[upbeat rock music]
Richie?
Richie, wake up!
Oh, hey, Darce.
You're napping at noon?
Like father, like son.
I have to write a book report
on The Wonderful Wizard of Oz,
so I tried to read the book,
which put me to sleep.
Then I tried to watch the movie,
which also put me to sleep.
Well, if you're gonna start over,
I'll watch it with you.
[music starts] Ugh!
I can't get into old movies.
Everyone is dressed in black and white.
Richie, we have problems!
The stock market has plummeted one point!
Oh, good news. It's back up.
Oh, no, it's down.
Murray, I have a book report to write.
So I need to get through this movie.
The Wonderful Wizard of Oz.
A literary classic.
You read the book?
Pfft! No way. That thing's over 200 pages.
Seen the movie?
I can't get into black and white.
I'm a man who requires brilliant color.
Sure, you are.
Irona, I need a favor.
Anything at all, Master Richie.
I need you to do my book report.
My moral processor will not
allow me to help you cheat.
Understood.
Oh, wanna have some fun?
Ooh, like feasting our eyes
on all the hot new models
down at the home appliance store?
Better.
I was thinking it'd be a ton of fun
if you read The Wonderful Wizard of Oz
then wrote a three to four page report
on the plot and themes of the book.
That book is based on factual
errors and erroneous science.
Irona, you have to accept
that Oz is a magical place
where lions talk, witches exist,
and scarecrows come alive.
I do not have a problem with any of that.
What gets me is the Tin Woodman rusting.
Tin is one of the most corrosion
resistant metals in existence.
Dad!
Have you ever read
The Wonderful Wizard of Oz?
Oh, it's my favorite book!
I know it by heart.
By heart, huh? Wanna tell me all about it?
Once upon a time, there was
a puppet named Pinocchio.
My name is Richie Rich,
and I'm just a normal kid...
except that I have
a trillion dollars.
You see, I used all
the vegetables I never ate
to create a new energy source
and sold it for a lot of money.
[cha-ching]
Now I live in a huge mansion
with my own amusement park,
race car, and personal robot maid.
And I have my family
and the best friends in the world
to share my fortune with--
my dad,
my jealous sister, Harper,
my money manager, Murray,
and my money spender, Darcy.
I guess you could say
by not eating my vegetables
I became the richest
and luckiest kid in the world!
Oh, guess what?
I met our neighbor
at the next mansion over.
Turns out he's a rapper.
I never thought those dudes
wrapping gifts at the mall
made that much money.
Just a guess, but...
I'm thinking he's a musician.
Pff. I don't know. His name's Bulldozah.
Ha. Sounds like a seasonal
gift-wrapper to me.
[breathing hard] Bulldozah?
He's a famous musician.
I own all of his music.
Well, I stream it for free,
but I love him!
I'm glad, 'cause I set up a playdate
for you and his little boy Tahj.
Playdate? Dad, I'm not seven.
I know. You're...older than that.
I'm really bad a guessing ages.
Dang, who's the babe?
I am not a babe. I am a robot.
A woman with no emotions? Yes, please.
Richie, this is Tahj.
- I thought he was 7.
- I thought he was 16.
I'm really bad at guessing ages.
How dare you think you're
going to give me a "B" in gym
and ruin my perfect GPA!
- Harper, I've got great news!
- What is it, Tulip?
I'm kind of in the middle
of a breakdown here.
Coach McHale told me
I'm getting my very first "A" ever!
Thanks again, Coach.
You're getting an "A" in gym?
Okay, Tulip, I can't believe
these words are coming out of my mouth,
but I need your help.
I totally believe those words
were coming out of your mouth.
You won't believe these words
are coming out of my mouth.
So, what do you call a dummy
who has wood for brains?
I don't know, buddy,
what do you call a dummy
who has wood for brains?
Tulip!
Way to step on my punch line, toots.
As impressive as your
ventriloquism skills are,
I need you to focus.
I can't get a "B" in gym,
so I need you to train me and prepare me
and do whatever it takes to get me an "A".
I'm sorry,
but as Coach McHale always says,
you have to do this on your own.
Tulip, I'm your best friend.
I'll help you, but shhh. He's right there.
That was ridiculous, Tahj.
Thanks again for taking us
to your dad's concert.
You totally have his good looks,
and I'm hoping that one day
you'll be getting his money, too.
That was so cool.
I've never gotten to hang out
backstage before.
I have. At my third grade piano recital.
Madame Claudette had a spread
of dairy-free string cheese.
Needless to say, it was pretty wild.
Sounds like a crazy night.
Evening. I was still in bed by 8:00.
Later, Richie. Bye, Tahj.
So, you go to all your dad's concerts?
Yeah, my mom pays me to make sure
he doesn't flirt with any girls.
My dad also pays me not
to say a word to my mom.
I make out like a bandit.
It's so cool that your dad's a rap star.
Yeah, it's sick. Just the other day,
Pharrell popped into my room
and was like, "Yo, where's
the bathroom in this place?"
Well, I would have loved
to have met your dad today,
but I'm sure he disappeared
off to some after-party.
He disappeared because he wasn't there.
What you saw was just a hologram.
- Seriously?
- He figures why perform
when you can cash checks sitting
around in your pajamas
watching home renovation shows?
My dad does the same thing.
Except for the cashing checks part.
Well, listen, I gotta write a book report.
Hey, you haven't seen
The Wonderful Wizard of Oz, have you?
No, but I wouldn't turn in
a plain old book report.
Not if you want a really good grade.
Okay, what does a really good grade mean,
'cause I'm totally cool with a "B".
These days, teachers need to be dazzled
by flashy multimedia presentations,
or autographed pictures of your dad,
and I don't think the second
one's gonna work for you.
So, uh, what, exactly,
does a flashy multimedia
presentation entail?
Tahj...
What happened to my room?
This isn't your room anymore.
It's your movie set.
Hey, if you need a nap,
hit your trailer out back.
It's the small one next
to my personal trainer's.
I don't know anything
about making a movie.
Now, if you have any questions
about the movie-making process,
I'm your man.
I spend a lot of time on sets.
Mostly like in my dad's trailer
practicing the flute,
- but I was there.
- Um, excuse me, Mr. Director,
but I believe I've been miscast.
I would make a great Cowardly Lion.
Sorry, Scarecrow. I'm the Lion.
But I'm terrified of everything.
It even took me 40 minutes
just to work up the nerve
to have this conversation.
This is humiliating. I don't do gingham.
Preach, sister. I do not do tin.
Thanks for trying to help, Tahj,
but maybe I should just write the paper.
I'm not ready to direct
a major motion picture.
I'd keep that to yourself, Double R.
Confidence is everything.
Says the Cowardly Lion.
Okay, we are going to learn
a few sports today.
How about we start with fencing?
I thought you weren't allowed
to handle sharp objects.
Maybe we should start with a sport
that doesn't involve swords.
You don't use swords. You use foils.
We can use my leftovers from last night.
Which are wrapped in foil.
- Yeah, I don't think...
- En garde.
Stop, stop, stop! I surrender.
Why aren't you fighting back?
Is it because you're distracted
by the smell of the ravioli?
'Cause I kinda am.
I wasn't fighting back
'cause when you came at me,
all these thoughts rushed to my head like,
"Don't get hurt. Why did I agree to this?
I'm kinda hungry."
That's why you are bad at sports.
The key to athletics is clearing your mind
and not thinking at all.
Huh. No wonder you're so good at this.
[cha-ching]
And...action?
Come on, Scarecrow.
Let's mosey on down
this road of yellow bricks.
Wait! Those bricks are gold!
[dog whimpers]
I do not care what we do,
for I don't have a brain.
I might not be smart,
but I sure am courageous.
Nothing scares me.
Not germs from rented costumes
or spur of the moment small talk
or early onset gingivitis.
Yep, not scared.
Oh, my, behold! It is a Tin Woodman.
Do you know the way to the Wizard
or perhaps the tall and handsome Lion?
Mmm, I cannot speak because,
despite being made of tin, I am rusted.
Perhaps the reason why I can't
speak is not the rust
but my bewilderment
at the indiscriminate rewriting
of the laws of science.
[engine purrs]
Oh, my, was that a lion's roar?
[engine roars]
That roar was from the 9-cylinder engine
on my minibike.
'Sup, Dorothy? Want a ride?
- Heck, yeah.
- Cut!
Tahj, what are you doing?
You're supposed to be a Cowardly Lion.
I'm spicing things up, baby.
Now sit back and enjoy the show.
And I'd sit really far back
when I wrestle the alligator in Act II.
Alligator? [sighs]
Guys, we have to stick
to what the internet says is in the book.
Well, why should I have to wear gingham
if Tahj gets to wear leather
and look all cool?
- I do look good, huh?
- I'm not complaining.
If they get to change their characters,
I get to change mine.
No one is changing anything.
Guys, we need to stick
to what's in the book.
Now, has anyone read the book?
Anyone seen the movie?
Next up in your training
is enter your room.
Okay, next step is further into your room.
- The next step--
- Tulip!
We've been doing this
all the way down the hall.
Speed it up.
How is coming to my bedroom
going to clear my mind?
It's not. Your tablet is.
No! Tulip!
What were you thinking?
My life's work is on here!
As are some concerned letters
to neurologists
that you really shouldn't see.
The point is you just reacted
and caught the tablet.
You didn't stop to think
about getting hurt
or why you agreed to this, or how is Tulip
able to make her voice come out
of the dummy like that?
Maybe she's thinking, "How is that dummy
able to get his voice to
come out of Tulip like that?"
That was amazing.
You actually know what you're doing.
As a kid, I swallowed
a talking Henry doll.
And have been able to do
the voice ever since.
I meant the teaching me to react thing.
I didn't have a single thought in my head
other than catching my tablet.
Tulip, you've taught me to be...uh...
- Uh...
- Exactly!
Okay, is there any chance
I can get a decent version
of the scene where
Dorothy and the Scarecrow
meet the Tin Woodman?
You mean the Tungsten Carbide Woodman.
Irona, that's not your costume.
Now it is. If Tahj is updating
his character, so am I.
A woodman today wouldn't wear tin.
They would be fitted in
ultra-dense tungsten carbide.
It is the top choice of metal
enthusiasts worldwide.
This is for class,
and I'd really like to stick
to what's in the book.
And...tornado, munchkins...
blah, blah, blah,
yeah, no tungsten carbide.
Bonjour, Monsieur.
Okay, Darcy, why are you speaking French?
[speaking French]
But you're, uh, Dorothy from Kansas.
Not anymore.
I feel like my Dorothy
would be from Paris,
and would be named Veronique.
Action.
[crash]
[glass shatters]
Tahj, why did you
just leap through my window?
I didn't.
My stuntman did.
But this is my book report--
not an action movie.
If you want it to be good,
it's gotta be both.
I don't go for good
when it comes to school.
I go for good enough.
Now, how about we take it down a bit?
- I think that's a bad--
- Okay, thanks.
And action.
Bonjour, Mademoiselle Woodman.
Would you like to accompany me
to go visit the Wizard?
Since I am rust-resistant tungsten carbide
and have no need for a heart,
keep moving, little lady.
But time is running out.
We need you, Tungsten Woman.
Society needs you. You're our last hope.
The asteroid the evil space robots
sent hurtling towards earth
is gonna be here in minutes!
Evil space robots?
For once it would be really cool to see
a positive role model for young robots.
Did someone say "cool"?
You know what else is cool?
Delicious soft-serve cones
and low-cal frozen yogurt
at Mr. Ice Creamie's.
Murray, what are you doing?
Making us some money
with product placement.
I get 35 bucks every time
I mention Mr. Ice Creamie's.
Try their new prickly pear sorbet--
now thorn-free.
We need to start over.
Thanks, Tahj,
for finally being reasonable.
We need to shoot this in 3-D.
That will make the intergalactic
laser fight really pop.
Not to mention your muscles.
This is not a movie. It's my book report,
which is due tomorrow!
[singsong] Speaking of tomorrow,
free sprinkles
with the purchase of any cone
at Mr. Ice Creamie's.
Offer not valid on rainbow.
That's it! Everyone off my set.
I mean out of my room!
Hey, buddy, whatcha doing?
My book report.
Richard Rich, I'm disappointed in you.
You can't go through life
paying people off.
Even though, I suppose,
you actually could.
It's just... I made a mistake.
I had this report due, and
I didn't want to read the book,
so I thought I could dazzle
my teacher into a good grade.
Now there's a blockbuster movie
shooting in my room.
Awesome! Is it in 3-D?
I love it when stuff's jumping out at ya.
Now it is, because I'm no longer involved
in making my own book report.
My friends are up there going wild.
Well...
that's what happens when you try
to take the easy way out.
Sometimes you need to take initiative
and do things for yourself.
It's the one thing I tried
to instill in you
is the value of hard work.
Well, time for my morning nap.
Thanks, Dad. I get it.
I'm going to march up to my room
and kick everyone out.
Then I'm gonna do my book report
for myself.
Yeah, hard work.
Turn the light off on your way out.
[cha-ching]
How dare you give me a "B"!
Harper, why are you so upset?
Because the perfect GPA that
I've had since kindergarten
is now gone!
But I thought you got an "A" in gym.
I did, but thanks to you,
I cleared my mind so well
I blinked on my history exam.
History is useless.
That stuff already happened.
They should be making us
take future class.
Tulip, don't make me put
a picture of you on this bag.
Calm down. I can tutor you in history.
Tulip!
How is this supposed to
help me in history?
I don't know. It worked for gym.
All right, guys, this is
the scene where T-Nice
bare-knuckle brawls
the time-traveling dinosaur
while dodging laser beams from space
and diffusing the bomb
strapped to his true love.
And action.
Hey, T. rex.
I'm about to make you extinct.
Again.
That's enough. This book report is...
[zapping]
Ah, laser beam!
You're napping at noon?
Like father, like son.
Whoa...deja vu.
Huh? I don't speak French.
Richie, we have problems.
The stock market has plummeted one point!
Oh, good news. It's back up.
Oh, no, it's down.
Okay, this is weird.
I met our neighbor.
They have a seven-year-old, too.
Dude, I'm not seven.
Really weird.
Master Richie.
Let me guess. Tin doesn't rust.
That is true,
but I was just going to offer
you some warm cookies.
Okay, I have to ask.
We weren't filming a movie
in here today, were we?
No...
Okay, I had the craziest dream
we were filming a movie
for my book report,
and you and you
and you and you were in it,
and even you were there,
and I had just met you.
He's Bulldozah's son.
Bulldozah's some famous
gift wrapper down at the mall.
I know who he is.
I've watched every episode
of his family's reality show.
I love The Bulldozah Bunch.
By the way,
are you really scared of balloons?
No, of course not. Why?
There aren't any in here, are there?
So we were making a movie version of
The Wonderful Wizard of Oz?
You are aware there already is one.
Everyone's seen it.
It's the best movie ever.
Wait, you've all seen it?
- Yeah.
- Yes!
- Classics!
- For reals?
Although making a movie
book report is not a bad idea.
These days, teachers need to be dazzled.
And so do dads who don't think
their kids have any talent.
Hmm, we could turn a quick buck
by landing some product placement.
I don't think that's such a good idea.
Let me guess.
You think I should read the book
and write a paper.
Pfft! That's way too much work.
If it were me, I'd just slide some cash
in an envelope and take the easy "A".
- Are you serious?
- No.
Read the book and write the report.
If there's anything
I've tried to teach you,
it's the value of hard work.
[yawns] Well, I'm beat.
I think it's time for my mid-morning nap.