[tires squeal]
[coughing]
Winner!
Irona, you just got smoked!
I guess you all got smoked.
Tahj, why aren't you
waving the checkered flag?
I did, but Irona jogged
in here six minutes ago.
Six minutes and seven seconds,
but who's counting?
Here, Richie, you earned
another participation trophy.
Great, just what I need.
Another stupid participation trophy.
Well, after that display,
you're certainly not getting
the sportsmanship award.
- Richie!
- What's up, boo?
Richie, I have
a huge test tomorrow,
and it's impossible to study
when all I hear is the whine of an engine.
Oh, that wasn't an engine.
That was Richie whining about losing.
I'm just trying to have some fun.
You know, that feeling you get when...
Actually, I'm not sure
you've ever felt that before.
Oh, I know the feeling.
I felt it every second
of the three years before you were born.
I'll show you some fun.
This Friday, me and you. My new car.
We can't go anywhere because
I don't have my permit yet,
but we can watch a movie
on the little screen.
Richie, I'm asking you nicely.
Please keep it down or you'll be sorry.
Harper, you can't put "please"
in front of a threat
and call it nice.
Message received.
Speaking of messages received,
so we're on for my driveway, 8:00?
I'll take that gesture as a thumbs up.
So what should we do now?
Obviously, no more racing.
Right, no more... You'll never catch me!
[tires squeal]
I've got some shopping to do,
so just take this.
My name is Richie Rich,
and I'm just a normal kid.
Except that I have a trillion dollars.
You see, I used all
the vegetables I never ate
to create a new energy source
and sold it for a lot of money.
Now I live in a huge mansion
with my own amusement park,
race car, and personal robot maid.
And I have my family and
the best friends in the world
to share my fortune with.
My dad, my jealous sister, Harper,
my money manager, Murray,
and my money spender, Darcy.
I guess you could say
by not eating my vegetables,
I became the richest
and luckiest kid in the world.
I don't understand how you beat me.
Are you cheating?
I do not think I am
the one that's cheating.
Master Richie,
I have a phone call for you.
Hey, Irona, is he the loser
you keep destroying in the race?
Sorry, wrong call.
This is your phone call.
Richie Rich! What up, dude?
It's Khalil. Khalil Woods.
I can't believe you're calling me!
You're my second favorite
basketball player.
I've always been a big LeBron guy.
What about that Kevin Durant dude
you're always talking about?
And that Blake Griffin fellow?
Shh!
Hey, Richie, what's up...
Khalil Woods!
Can I get a hug?
So what's going on?
My birthday's coming up.
I want you to be there.
Thanks, Khalil!
This is so cool!
Whatevs.
I mean, I'll be there.
But... whatevs.
My first Hollywood star-studded party!
And it's about to go down.
It's at Bonito Bowl-A-Rama.
No way! That place is so...
Wait, where?
I was having this huge bash
at the Staples Center,
but my money manager
made me rein it in.
Oh, BTW, my man Murray suggests
bringing a little cash
for shoe rental... and food.
And quarters
if you have to use the bathroom.
Murray!
Well, if you prefer,
you could have your party on my yacht.
What-- Of course.
That would be amazing!
Man, this is so generous and unexpected.
You were right, Murray. He fell for it.
This is amazing!
I can't believe we get to go
to Khalil Woods' party!
I know. A few weeks ago,
I couldn't even get invited to
my best friend's birthday party.
For the last time, it wasn't a party.
It was just an informal get-together
with a piñata and cake.
[doorbell rings]
Hello!
I don't know what you're here
to sell, but I'll take some.
I am Tulip.
Ah, a beautiful girl
named after a beautiful flower.
Flower?
I'm named Tulip
because I have two lips.
One above my chin,
and one under
my breathing holes.
I think I love you.
Is Harper here?
I need her help.
Haven't seen her,
but I'm sure I could be
your knight in pleated khakis.
I'm about to fail math,
and if I do,
the school's going
to kick me off the soccer team.
I can help,
because I happen to specialize
in numerical concepts
and statistical application.
I need help in math.
Okay, I have to ask:
Would you mind taking a selfie with me?
You're exactly the kind of girl
I've always dreamt
of telling people I was dating.
Guys, I have something really
important to talk to you about.
I need to go away for the night.
Big things are finally
starting to happen for me,
and I think you guys are going to be
really proud of your old man.
- Did you get a job?
- A girlfriend?
Better!
I got first pick
in my fantasy football draft!
Who's watching us?
You are not dropping us off
at the kennel again.
How was I supposed to know
it was a place for dogs?
The ad said it was a place
to leave loved family members
to be fed, bathed, and dipped
for fleas and ticks.
- Tell me we can just stay here.
- That's the plan.
I figured Harper could be in charge.
- Yes!
- No!
You can't do this to me.
I don't need Harper
to tell me what to do.
I have Irona.
Yes, because that is how
our relationship works.
Well, you'll do what your sister says,
or I'll take Irona away for two months.
- No!
- Two months off?
I guess I could live with that punishment.
Well, you won't exactly be off.
You'll be helping me. For starters,
you can shave the bunions off my feet.
No!
You know, Dad, the kennel's
not sounding so bad after all.
I think we have a good plan.
Out you go, dad.
Whatever Harper says, goes,
because she's the boss.
Is that how that works?
I don't know, I've never had
a boss before.
Heel.
Irona, I refuse to wear a leash.
It was different at the kennel
because they made it up to me
in belly rubs.
I'm just making sure you
keep in line with your sister.
Do an image search for bunions,
you will understand.
Relax, Harper's only in charge
for two days.
She may be jealous of my success,
but she's not crazy.
- Out of my room.
- Uh, this is my room.
No, this used to be your room.
But now I'm moving into it
because I'm in charge.
Out you go.
You heard the girl. Out we go.
Do you really expect me
to give up my room
to go sleep in yours?
It's pink and smells like evil.
Who said anything about my room?
You're bunking in the elevator.
Fine, whatever. Come on, Irona.
Ah, ah, ah.
You're not going anywhere, Irona.
From now on, you don't listen to him.
You only do what Harper says.
This-- This is ridiculous!
Wait!
I love you, Master Richie.
Don't you do that.
Don't you say your good-byes.
I am so cold.
Never let go. Promise me.
And never let go of that promise.
I promise.
My heart will go on and on and on...
Stop reciting lines from Titanic.
Irona, you don't even have a heart.
I don't know why I have to learn
these complex formulas anyway.
I'm never going to use this stuff
in real life.
Tulip, you can do this. One plus one...
Here's a hint: The answer's in your name.
Steinhoff.
Okay, let's just say you and I
ended up married,
assuming you agree to keeping
our finances separate,
and we had a boy and a girl.
How many children would we have?
- Yes!
You said, "Yes"!
Now, before we start
the wedding planning,
you're going to need
to meet my mother.
Just tell her her brisket is moist.
It won't be. Just tell her it is.
You're a funny little man.
I said "yes" because the pencil works.
That's good, isn't it?
I wouldn't say it's as good
as an acceptance
of my subtle marriage proposal,
but I'm happy you're happy.
Hey, Richie, I narrowed my outfit options
for tonight's party down to 50.
Whoa, what happened in here?
It's pink, and it smells like evil.
It's not evil. It's power.
Irona, another spritz of power.
As you wish, Queen Harper.
Where's Richie?
No one says that name in my presence!
Why are you talking like that?
Because I am in charge.
And for dramatic effect.
Mostly dramatic effect.
Now, you mentioned a party tonight.
Tell me more.
Richie and I were kinda,
sorta personally invited
to Khalil Woods' birthday party.
Richie thinks he's going to this party
without my permission?
- Uh...
- Come back!
Oh, I'm back, boo.
I've been waiting for you to come around.
Have you been sitting
in our hall this entire time?
Not if it's weird.
Okay, it's only an hour before your test.
Desperate times call
for desperate measures.
Let's run away to France!
Forget it. I'm going to fail math,
get kicked off the soccer team,
and let down my teammates.
Jenn, Mallory, Racquel, Gina, Sam, Katie,
Shawna, Monica, Sharon,
Natalie, and Gladiolus.
I wish I had a pretty flower
name like Gladiolus.
Wait, how did you remember
all those names?
I made up a little song.
I'd sing it for you,
but I don't have my pitch pipe.
If you can memorize songs
about your teammates,
you can memorize songs about math.
Listen closely.
♪ One plus one is two, you see ♪
♪ And two plus one equals three ♪
♪ Wicky, wicky, wicky, wah ♪
I get it! One plus one is two.
Two plus one equals three.
And three plus one
is wicky, wicky, wicky, wah.
After a couple more verses,
that will be good enough to pass.
If I do, I'm gonna plant one
on you with this two lips.
I'm gonna get my first kiss before 30!
Take that, Dad.
Richie, what are you doing in here?
Conserving oxygen.
Harper banished me in here,
but as long as she thinks
I'm in this elevator,
it'll be easy to sneak out to my yacht.
The most important thing is,
she can't know about Khalil's party.
What did you do?
Okay, I have
a confession to make.
[Harper over PA] Have fun locked
in your metal box.
It looks like I'm the one
who's going to Khalil's party.
Harper, no!
- Darcy, you told her?
- I didn't say a word.
Then what were you
going to confess?
There was one time where
I spent your money
without your permission.
Whew, feels so much better
having that out in the open.
I am so sorry for letting
Harper know
about Khalil's party.
I feel horrible
that she's not letting you go.
It's okay.
I don't blame you.
Good, because she didn't
mention anything
about me not going,
and I don't want to flake
and let Khalil down.
I have to get out of here.
Just...a little...higher...
Got it.
All right, Darcy. I'll pull you up.
Having seen your arms,
I'm just going to go ahead
and use the jet pack.
I'm ready for the party.
I command you to tell me
how beautiful I look.
You look... beautiful.
You're just saying that.
I mean, don't you love these shoes?
I feel like they were made for this dress.
And don't you think this color
totally brings out my eyes?
Maybe I need a necklace,
but what if it's going to be
cold on the yacht?
I just realized you are covered in lint.
Irona, stop!
You are banished to the dungeon!
You are aware
we do not have a dungeon.
Yeah, it's just a basement,
but the air circulation's,
like, really bad,
so it's kind of dungeon-like.
Richie, make sure you're decent.
I need to ride your bedroom
up to my bedroom.
[silently mouthing words]
You know, Queen Harper,
if you are heading
to what is now your room,
the secret passage would save time
and prevent you from running into Tahj,
who, according to my sensors,
is standing outside your bedroom
with a box of chocolates.
Thanks.
[beep]
Hey. Let me out!
The air circulation is horrible in here.
It's like a dungeon!
Have a lovely evening, Harper.
Richie!
Thanks, Irona. That showed a lot of heart.
Master Richie, you are no picnic,
but under that,
you are the most amazingly,
astounding, wonderful boy
that I have ever known.
- Irona, I...
- No!
Let me try and get this out.
I am no idiot. I know how the world works.
- [record scratch]
- You're both idiots.
What is it with you two and Titanic?
Oh, that was from the movie!
For a second there,
that got kind of weird.
Hi.
Hello, my little angel.
- I failed.
- What?
No! How is this possible?
You knew that song so well.
Are you sure you wrote down
the correct numbers?
Yes, and I still failed.
Not only did I get a 0%,
but the teacher made it
into a frowny face.
This doesn't make any sense.
Can I see the test?
Okay, but don't look at the frowny face.
- It'll make you wanna cry.
- I already wanna cry.
"Identify the verb in the sentence"?
I put three, but he still marked it wrong.
Three isn't a verb. It's a number.
And this isn't a math test. It's grammar.
Well, whatever it is,
I'm getting kicked off the soccer team,
and I just bought this new soccer bat.
Hello?
Richie? Harper?
[sighs] Please tell me I didn't go
into the wrong house again.
[Harper] Dad?
Let me out, I'm stuck!
- [knocking]
- Harper?
What are you doing in there?
Richie locked me in there.
He is out of control.
You need to take away his robot
and make her shave your bunions.
Actually, the one who was
out of control is Harper.
She took over Richie's bedroom,
banished him to the elevator,
and made me wear this degrading pantsuit.
Silence, Irona!
Harper, why are you talking like that?
Because I am in charge now.
And for dramatic effect.
Mostly dramatic effect.
Harper, I trusted you.
I thought you were mature enough
to look after your brother,
and clearly you're not.
I hoped you would take that
responsibility more seriously
while I was hitting Vegas
for my fantasy football draft.
I guess you're right, Dad.
I did get a little carried away
with my first taste of power.
Just to clarify,
there will be no bunion shaving
for me, correct?
- I'm sorry I let you down.
- Thank you.
But I think your brother's
the one you should apologize to.
You're right. I should do that right now.
To get it off my chest.
And hopefully meet Khalil Woods
while I'm at it.
Khalil Woods?
He's my favorite basketball player,
which explains why
everyone laughed at me
when I drafted him in fantasy football.
Now, try to act cool.
We don't want Khalil thinking
we're a couple of crazed fans.
Nobody... nobody...
Shocked Emoji! There's Khalil!
Hey, what's up, Richie?
Hey, Khalil. Happy birthday.
OMG, I am such a big fan of yours.
Is that Kevin Durant?
Outta my way!
Hey, this yacht is sick, Richie.
Thanks for hooking it up.
Oh, if LeBron asks,
this is my yacht, named Nothin' But Net.
What's up, Khalil? Happy birthday, bro.
Thanks for inviting me.
Cool, man, no problem.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wait, who are you?
T-Nice. Tahj?
- Tahj Stokes?
- Bulldozah's kid.
Oh, cool man.
Wait, is your dad here?
I assume you're his plus one.
Yeah, or he's mine.
I forget how we worked it.
So, Richie, is Harper here?
I hope not. Is that a shooting star?
[Harper] Richie-e-e-e-e-e-e!
[splash]
[people gasp]
Harper, I know you haven't
been yourself lately,
but put the jellyfish down.
No one needs to get hurt.
It's too late for that.
This thing did a number on my leg.
How dare you lay a tentacle my woman!
Ah! It burns!
Harper, let's not make a scene.
[yelling]
More of a scene.
Richie, I came out here to apologize.
I realized I got a little carried away
with the responsibility that Dad gave me,
and I had no right to treat you
the way that I did.
Uh, Khalil?
We need to call the Coast Guard.
I think the jellyfish poison's
got to her brain.
Richie, I'm serious. I'm really sorry,
and I came all the way out here
to tell you that.
And to say hey to Khalil Woods.
Hey, Khalil, huge fan.
You're my sixth favorite
basketball player,
- after LeBron, Kevin...
- I get it, I get it.
But you're ruining my party,
so you need to hit the road or the water.
Hey, Khalil, this is my yacht,
and she's my sister.
- So she can stay.
- [laughs]
Richie's just playin', bron-bron.
Nothin' But Net is my yacht.
Hey, look, she can stay,
but chill on
the "this is my yacht" stuff.
These guys already talk
bad enough about my jump shot.
I'm not sure I deserved that, but thanks.
No problem. I owed it to you.
Why did you owe me?
Well, when you locked me
in the elevator,
I sorta, kinda told Tahj
you'd go on that date with him.
[upbeat rock music]
♪ ♪