Irona, sports drink me.
Right away, master Richie.
Richie, I'm glad you have
the protective gear on,
but you should really be wearing
a bracelet
noting your allergy to milk.
You can't be too safe.
Where'd you learn how to skate like that?
I didn't learn it.
I was born with it.
It's called natural talent, baby.
[skateboard whirs]
Having a smart board also helps.
Hmm, something that requires
zero athletic ability?
I may have found my sport.
You're allergic to plutonium?
When are you in contact with plutonium?
Don't ask questions
you don't want the answers to.
Irona, get Murray some ice, please.
Right away, master Richie.
So, Darce, you wanna give it a try?
I would, but I don't want
to break anything.
You won't get hurt.
I'm not worried about breaking a bone.
I'm worried about breaking a heel.
Do you know how much you paid
for these shoes?
Irona, confiscate Darcy's credit card.
Right away, master Richie.
Irona, do you have my sports drink
and Murray's ice?
Right away, master Richie.
She's either broken
or has taken on the work ethic
of my mother.
I'll see if I can shock her
into a different response.
Irona, Murray is madly in love with you,
and you're marrying him tonight.
Right away, master Richie.
She's definitely broken.
This isn't good.
So can I still marry her or...
My name is Richie Rich,
and I'm just a normal kid--
except that I have
a trillion dollars.
You see, I used
all the vegetables I never ate
to create a new energy source
and sold it for a lot of money.
[cha-ching]
Now I live in a huge mansion
with my own amusement park,
race car, and personal robot maid.
And I have my family and
the best friends in the world
to share my fortune with:
My dad,
my jealous sister, Harper,
my money manager, Murray,
and my money spender, Darcy.
I guess you could say,
by not eating my vegetables,
I became the richest and
luckiest kid in the world.
Wait, Irona, don't go!
"If you jump, I jump. Remember?
I can't turn away without
knowing you'll be all right."
It's from Titanic.
It's their thing.
It's weird. We know.
"Come on, give me your hand.
You don't want to do this."
Right away, master Richie.
Yeah, she's toast.
Take her away.
It'll be all right, Richie.
She'll only be gone while they repair her.
As a loaner, the company is sending me
some stupid mini-model called "Urona."
I don't want a Urona.
I want my Irona.
She's so good at coughing
to cover up my farts.
[coughs]
Excuse me, I had something in my throat.
I don't think
I want some strange robot here.
I'm gonna call them and tell
them to keep their Urona.
Hello, master Richie, I am Urona.
Welcome to my home.
So glad to have you here.
Oscar Wilde was born in Ireland.
Born in Ireland. Oscar Wilde--
Dad, what are you doing in my room?
I could ask you the same thing.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I need to reread my English assignment.
I see that you're reading Oscar Ireland.
Did you know that he was born in the wild?
It's Oscar Wilde, who was born in Ireland,
but that was remarkably close for you.
How'd you know that?
Ah, I was a big Oscar Wilde
guy back in high school.
I was quite the student until I...
burnt myself out.
You used to study?
I don't believe it.
- It's true.
You actually remind me
a lot of myself as a kid.
The studying, the obsessing
about getting into college,
the shaving of the legs.
Dad!
What? I was a swimmer.
Just a few times a year down
at the community pool,
but when I went, I really moved.
So what happened to you?
I nicked my knee and decided
it wasn't worth the risk.
I meant about school.
Oh, well, growing up, I never gave myself
enough time for fun.
So one day, I walked out of school
and haven't picked up a book since.
Oh, my gosh.
I can't believe you used to be like me.
That means I could end up like...
Oh, my gosh!
Listen, you're a smart girl, Harp.
I'm sure you'll figure something out.
I just wanted to give you
a heads-up that sometimes
working too hard is
the worst thing you can do.
Oh, is that why you do absolutely nothing?
That's right.
You think Richie is liking
his replacement robot?
Wow.
I'm really liking my replacement robot.
Hard to tell.
Master Richie--
Oh, please, call me Richie.
Or just call me.
Here's my phone number.
What does Richie see in her?
Sure, she's pretty
and waits on his every need,
but she's incapable of feelings
or emotions.
You don't understand guys, do you?
I can't watch this.
Richie, would you like a snack?
Are you hungry?
Let me grab you something.
I just realized, I have no idea
where the kitchen is.
But I brought you this priceless vase.
Thank you, but I do not need a vase.
Of course. How stupid of me.
Allow me to clean that up.
No, no, please. Leave it.
Let's get to know each other.
Tell me something about yourself.
I have 7,000 twin sisters,
I was born in a box,
and I rust if left outside.
You too?
We have so much in common.
So wanna go walk
through my corn maze?
Maybe we'll get lucky and find Tom.
Who's Tom?
Oh, just some guy who got lost
in my corn maze.
But if you don't like corn,
I also have a green bean maze.
I'm sorry, but I do not think
that would be appropriate.
I am a robot, and you are my boss.
And I am here to work for you.
I do not want to be unprofessional.
But I've never felt this way before.
I am sorry, but my programming
will not allow me to date my boss.
In that case, you're fired.
Why is she still here?
I thought Richie fired her.
I hope she's not waiting
for her last paycheck.
She didn't do anything.
I can still hear you guys.
Oh, we know.
Is it hot in here,
or did your internal fan system
just crash?
We've been over this.
I cannot go out with you.
I'm not taking a no for an answer.
Let me try again.
Not again.
This will be 12 times.
I can't force quit you.
Ooh, that one was pretty good.
Hey, Felix, over here.
Actually, Darcy, I ordered that
for Urona.
Oh, Richie.
You got that for me?
Darcy always tells me diamonds
are a girl's best friend.
I'm hoping they are a robot girl's too.
They are.
I can't believe Richie bought her that!
You're upset that he's spending money?
Yeah, that's my job.
Well, getting upset about it is my job.
Stay in your lane.
Richie, can we have a word with you?
One sec, Darce.
I'm about to give Urona a gift.
[both] Another one?
Richie, you really do not need
to spoil me like this,
but you do have me curious.
What is it?
It's...
a brand-new car!
[both sobbing]
I didn't know robots
could cry tears of happiness.
They can't!
It should've been me!
Urona, the last six hours
have been the best six hours
of my life.
I want to buy you the world!
No!
Would you be my girlfriend?
No.
But I will be your robot-friend.
Yes!
[imitating robot]
I will make you so happy.
Please do not ever do that again.
Dad, you may have scared me
into having fun,
but I'm not sure about tricycle jousting.
Nothing is more fun
than tricycle jousting.
Nothing, I say!
But, dad--
Silence, dragon!
Let the games begin!
By the way, the nearest hospital
is on magnolia.
- Why would I need to know--
- Charge!
[squeaking]
[groans]
Are you okay?
Can't pedal in this armor.
Oh, I didn't know we started.
[screaming]
Hold on! Time out, dragon!
[screams]
That was awesome!
Hospital. Magnolia.
Quickly, dragon.
How does Richie not see
that that robot girl
is just using him for his money?
I think your friendship with him proves
that's always been a blind spot.
Where is he?
He said he finally had time
to hang out with us.
Here I am.
What are you wearing?
Urona took me shopping.
She said I look handsome in this.
Handsome's not the word I would've used.
Richie, we feel like
you're spending too much time with Urona.
That is such a human thing
of you to say, Murray.
Everybody knows time is
a manufactured conspiracy
to sell more watches.
By the way, do you know what time it is?
I'm supposed to meet Urona at 2:00.
I don't know.
Richie, we miss hanging out
with you like we did
before you fell for a...
robot.
We can still hang out. [gasps]
Maybe Urona can come.
She loves hanging out.
She's really good at hanging out.
Yeah, yeah, is there anything
Urona isn't great at?
Weirdly, stairs.
Well, if you'll excuse me,
I told Urona I'd take a course
in roboethics before I meet her mother.
Tonight's lecture is titled
"when a boy loves a robot."
Okay, that was awesome.
- But I think we're done with--
- Strike!
This is so much fun!
Yeah, fun.
Although, with first pick,
I should've chose
the ball costume.
So you ready to do something else?
Okay, maybe we can-- strike!
[grunts]
That never gets old.
Yeah. [chuckles] Never.
So do you want to, uh--
Strike!
[crash]
That was a good one, dad.
Okay, we're done bowling.
I mean, we've packed in
a lot of fun, but I need a nap.
I mean, I've been up
for three straight hours!
No time for rest.
I mean, we're already behind schedule.
We need to have more fun.
Skydiving took forever.
Hey, at least your chute opened.
Seriously, I need a break.
I get it, dad.
We've been going pretty hard,
and we could both probably use a...
water balloon fight!
No!
No, no, no!
Oh.
Well, we've lost him to the dark side.
How is love the dark side?
Any side that involves me
spending less of Richie 's money
is the dark side.
You and I can still hang out.
I guess we could.
Nah, we're not doing that.
I have missed you, baby!
Every time I see a dust bunny,
I think of you.
Nobody likes vacuuming that much.
Let's not jump to conclusions.
That doesn't mean anything.
That does.
I can't believe she's cheating on Richie!
With a vacuum cleaner!
We need to stick up for Richie
and confront her.
Right. I like it.
Let's do this.
Can you do the confronting?
That's not really my thing.
Well, well, well,
what do we have here?
[vacuum cleaner crashes]
Oh, sorry, baby.
Calling the vacuum "baby," that's weird.
I thought I was doing the confronting.
I got hit with a rush of testosterone.
The pills my doctor gave me
must be working.
I do not know what you think
you saw, but you saw it wrong.
Oh, yeah?
We saw you lay a thick smooch
on that vacuum.
That is not true.
Oh, it's true, lead lips!
We're not going to let
this happen to our friend.
Guys, stop.
Richie, your girlfriend
is dating someone else.
That's ridiculous.
You are my only man, Richie.
Well, that is technically true
because she's cheating with a vacuum,
but...
she is cheating nonetheless.
Richie, you have to believe us.
I'm your best friend, and Murray's...
here too.
Baby, my internal processor is yours.
I believe you, steely pie.
They're just jealous of our love.
I wish you guys could be happy for me.
Let's go grab
some software updates and relax.
Think we should go find
that vacuum and beat it up?
What's that going to solve?
Oh, I've just always wanted
to win a fight.
I feel like I have a good shot
against a home appliance.
I am back, master Richie!
I am fully repaired and feel like
I am king of the world!
It's good to have you back, Irona.
There's like an inch of dust
on everything.
Master Richie,
why are you wearing an apron
and holding a tray?
Did Urona crash on you?
Those minis--half the size,
less than half the reliability.
Hey, you watch your robot mouth.
Urona is amazing.
She's my robot-friend.
You are dating a robot?
Not that there is anything
wrong with that.
My cousin Steve is dating a human.
Thanksgivings are weird.
Well, I have to run.
Urona doesn't like me
talking to other robots.
Oh, and by the way,
this is your new uniform.
Urona picked it out.
A trash bag?
[elevator bell dings]
What is going on around here?
Urona is two-timing Richie with a vacuum.
We've tried to tell Richie,
but he won't listen to us.
And Urona's boyfriend
has a wicked left upholstery attachment.
Well, I will not stand
for someone doing this
to master Richie.
And this trash bag is not even in my size.
I am going to give that machine
a piece of my memory board.
Don't worry, Irona.
We have a plan to expose her,
but we need your help.
Normally, I do not follow
along with humans' plans
because they are flawed and filled
with logistical oversights.
But I will do anything to defend
the honor of master Richie.
I can assure you, this plan is flawless.
When do we start?
- Right now.
- Tomorrow.
Come on, dad! We're still playing!
Don't give up.
Can't...take...
any...more.
Fine. New game.
Sleep. Need nap.
No resting.
I will not allow myself to burn out.
We need to have more fun.
Are jumping jacks fun?
No.
We need to have more fun, quickly.
The fun is slipping away.
No more fun. I'm funned out!
Dad, get up.
Why is there a note
under my pillow that says
"Oscar Wilde, born in Ireland"?
You must have left it there.
But it's not in my writing,
and it's all misspelled.
No, this is a cliff note.
Maybe I did. I don't remember.
Dad, you just took another note.
What? No. No, I didn't.
"I was just like you as a kid"?
That's right. Me and you.
Two peas in a something.
Dad, why would you have to
script that whole conversation
we had if it were true?
All right,
I was nothing like you as a kid.
I didn't study.
I wasn't obsessed
about getting into college.
I never shaved my--
well, I never did those first two things.
That is such a relief.
I mean, I can't believe you lied to me
but such a relief.
I'm sorry I lied to you,
but you're so stressed out.
I just wanted to make sure
you're enjoying your life.
I am enjoying my life.
Now let's try something that I enjoy.
"It was the best of times,
it was the worst of times..."
[snoring]
We'll finish it tomorrow.
Another chocolate-covered bolt, my sweet?
Richie, we need to apologize
to you and Urona.
Well, thanks, guys. That means a lot.
[vacuum whirring]
Do not mind me.
I am just going to do some vacuuming
with this gorgeous new vacuum.
Irona, we don't need you
to vacuum right now.
I agree.
Put down the vacuum and walk away.
I don't know. It's pretty dirty in here.
So anyway, Urona, Darcy and I are so sorry
for falsely accusing you.
We can see in your eyes
that you would never cheat,
and that's the kind of robot
Richie deserves.
Ooh, you are so strong.
Irona, it's nice to see you
finally enjoying work,
but we're kind of having
a moment over here.
We just want to see Richie happy
because he's a really great, honest guy.
Wow.
That was the vacuum of my life.
Time to take this bad boy to another room.
Perhaps somewhere a little more...
dusty.
Get your hands off my man.
I'm right here, steely pie.
Go find yourself another vacuum.
This one's taken.
And why aren't you wearing your bag?
Urona, you really are cheating on me...
with a vacuum cleaner.
I'm so sorry, Richie.
I should go.
I'm going to miss you.
Thanks.
I'm gonna miss you too.
I was talking to the necklace.
Yeah, you better run, punk.
[vacuum whirs] We're cool.
Guys, I owe you an apology.
I got blinded by love and lost sight
of what's most important to me:
Our friendship.
[coughs]
Thanks, Irona.
It's good to have you back.
You guys are the best friends
I could ask for,
and I will never not trust you again.
Thanks, Richie.
As your friend, I am never
letting any gold-digging girl
near you again, and that's a promise.