[engine revving]
- Ahh!
- [crash]
- Sorry, guys!
I'm still getting used
to driving inside a mansion.
And driving.
Are you guys okay?
I'm good. The airbag broke my fall.
Darcy, the wagon doesn't have an airbag.
I meant Murray.
After that collision,
I need to make an appointment
with my chiropractor...
and my attorney.
Could have sworn my bedroom
was around here somewhere.
Let's ask her for directions.
That's Irona, my maid.
Wow. You are really hot.
My electrostatic super
capacitor tends to overheat.
Guess I should have mentioned
she's also a robot.
I splurged on the supermodel model.
I've never uttered these words in my life,
but money well spent.
This is Murray, my best friend
and money manager.
And this is Darcy, my other best friend.
Don't let her see my bank password.
We'll talk later.
[cha-ching]
Welcome to Richie's bedroom.
Wow! This place is awesome!
I can't believe you live here now.
I can't believe you paid for all of this!
Check it out.
It's got a dollar comforter.
You mean down?
No, I mean it's filled with dollars.
Master Richie's entire room is automated
and can be controlled by a push
of a button on his room remote.
Or roomote.
Chuckle. Chuckle.
Giggle.
Is that an aquarium?
Yep! Meet my new pet whales:
Dollar, Dollar, and Bill, y'all!
All you need is a bubbling treasure chest.
Over there.
Is that real gold?
And on a completely unrelated
note, do you have a snorkel?
[cash register dings]
My name is Richie Rich,
and I'm just a normal kid...
except that I have
a trillion dollars.
You see, I used all the vegetables
I never ate to create a new energy source
- and sold it for a lot of money.
- [cha-ching]
Now I live in a huge mansion
with my own amusement park, race car,
and personal robot maid.
And I have my family and the best friends
in the world to share my fortune with.
My dad, my jealous sister Harper,
my money manager Murray,
and my money spender Darcy.
I guess you could say
by not eating my vegetables,
I became the richest
and luckiest kid in the world!
[clattering]
Gold bar?
I wanted a candy bar!
Stupid machine...
[mouthing words]
Richie, I feel like
you're throwing money away.
Did get this basketball for free.
That's great!
When I bought
a professional basketball team.
Ugh!
I'm glad we still hang out,
even though you're rich now.
Of course! We're best friends.
Now, check this out!
Air ball!
No more air balls for me!
My engineers invented this
never-miss basketball hoop...
after seeing my jump shot...
Sick!
If you think that's cool,
you should see the bathrooms.
They were able to use the same
technology on the toilets!
Master Richie, I just received
a message from your father.
[father's voice] "Richie, please
come into the living room."
Irona, I know you have
the voice modulation software,
but please don't speak in my dad's voice.
Totally ruins the magic.
[shudders]
Ugh!
[engine revs]
[tires screech]
Uh, ha-ha... Dad?
This isn't our old house.
You don't have to sleep in the living room
or shower in the neighbor's sprinklers.
Richie, I'm a man
who doesn't require luxuries
like beds or indoor plumbing.
I can be happy on a couch.
I have to be, since I can't figure out
how to get in my bedroom with
that high-tech entry system.
It's just a doorknob.
And what's that crazy-looking
eye scanner device?
A peephole?
- Oh!
- [elevator bell dings]
Richie.
My room looks exactly
like the Harvard library.
And while I might appreciate
having a full-time librarian,
I wish she wouldn't shush me
every time I speak.
Shh!
I am not even in my room!
Harper, I knew how hard you've
been working to get in Harvard
so I thought
if I made your dream come true,
it'd make you happy!
You don't seem happy.
I want to get into the actual Harvard,
not a replica my slacker brother built.
It's not a replica!
I bought the actual library
building and had it moved here.
Well, most of it...
the crane dropped one of the walls,
so we had to replace it
with plywood and spackle.
[chortling]
Spackle.
That's a funny word.
Dad, I can't handle living
in this monument
to Richie's pathetically lucky success.
You should be happy for your brother.
Not only did he make a gajillion dollars,
but that doodad he invented
did something...
good for the planet.
Eliminated the need for carbon-based fuel.
Yeah, that.
All Richie did was catch
lightning in a bottle!
Literally! He just crammed
a bunch of uneaten vegetables
into a bottle that happened
to get struck by lightning.
Are you accusing me
of not knowing what I was doing
when I invented my
trap-electricity-in-vegetables
thingamajig?
Dad.
Why did you want to see us?
See you? I don't know.
Oh, wait, yeah, uh...
so I wanted to spend
some quality time together.
I feel really disconnected here.
What if we had a family dinner?
A family dinner?
Why am I being punished?
[cha-ching]
Guess what?
I hacked into your bank account
and had you buy you
a vertical wind tunnel.
BTW, your password was really weak,
so I went ahead and changed it for you.
Okay, what's the new one?
For security reasons, I can't tell you.
Richie, we have a problem.
It's your new jet.
Don't tell me
there are more engine issues.
Apparently, a solid gold jet
has trouble staying in the air.
#trillionaireproblems.
Jet or no jet,
we can still skydive with this.
Ahh!
[crash]
Aah!
Oh, no! Darcy crashed through the ceiling!
It's worse than you think.
Right above my room is a gorilla habitat.
[gorilla noises]
Of all the days to wear banana lip gloss.
You're in good hands, Darcy.
I downloaded an entire medical
library on Irona's hard drive.
Now, she's practically a doctor.
Before I do any more,
I will need proof of insurance.
Darcy, I feel bad that you
blasted through the ceiling
into my gorilla habitat...
and that my ceiling fan was on high.
I want to do something
to make this up to you.
I have just the thing!
A coupon for a free lemonade
at Corndog Larry's.
How about I score us three passes
to a concert of a lifetime?
Like the one and only U.S. show
of Swedish house sensation
Swedish House Sensation!
That's awesome!
He's the best deejay in the world!
Ow...
It hurts to get excited.
Maybe you didn't hear me.
Coupon.
Free lemonade.
Free.
[cha-ching]
Murray told me
you bought the concert tickets
and exactly how much they cost.
I can't wait for tomorrow night!
Me neither!
Now I just have to find
something to wear...
Irona, to the mall.
Richie.
I feel like you, Harp,
and I are drifting apart,
so I'm reinstituting
an old family tradition.
Dad, Harp and I are too old
to take baths together.
Starting tomorrow, I'm
bringing back family game night.
Tomorrow? I can't! I have plans!
Richie, when we moved here, we agreed.
Your house, my rules.
Cancel your plans.
Please!
I'd be willing to revisit the bath thing.
Of all the nights to have
a stupid family game night,
my dad picks the one night
I have concert tickets.
Spending quality time with family
is important for maintaining
meaningful relationships.
You may have a motherboard,
but you don't have to act like my mother.
Apologies, Master Richie.
Pops be straight trippin', yo.
Hey, Richie.
Guess who just beat Murray
in a game of HORSE--
the girl who can't use her extremities!
Well, I have some bad news
about Swedish House Sensation.
Oh, no. Don't tell me he's not going
to perform 'Bout Them Meatballs!
I love that song.
The beat makes me move my feet
like a wild man.
The problem is,
we can't go to the concert.
What?
Why? Do you have plans with
some new fancy rich friends?
By the way, if they need a money manager,
here's my card.
I knew once you became rich
you wouldn't want
to hang out with us anymore.
Those gorillas may have broken
84 of my bones,
but you broke my heart.
You didn't let me finish.
I was saying we can't go to the concert...
because it's gonna be here.
In my room.
It is?
That's the plan.
That I just came up with.
Master Richie, may I have a word?
I do not understand.
Are you canceling family game night?
Nope. I'm going to both.
I do not think that is a wise--
[ahem]
Get yours, son.
Word.
Hello! I am Swedish house sensation
Swedish House Sensation!
Whoa! Hello, you fine piece of
reinforced titanium alloy.
You are sure easy on the
multispectral optical sensors.
You are "bootiful" yourself,
but I must say,
there is a Mrs. House Sensation.
So what is having
Richie Rich bring me here?
He was hoping to convince you
to move tomorrow's show here.
Are you suggesting...
Oh, it... it's so hot in zis helmet.
You are human?
I am sorry, but moving
my concert here is not possible.
Maybe this will change your mind.
I will be here at 7:00.
But I cannot stay for after-party.
If I'm not home in time
for family game night,
my papa will give me
a swift kick in ze rumpa!
[background chatter]
[dance music playing]
Murray, where's Darcy?
I want to say hi before game night.
Game night? You mean the concert?
Guys! How do I look?
Oh... my... gauze.
I ordered a custom couture body cast
so I wouldn't look like an idiot.
Hope you kept the receipt.
Master Richie.
1 minute and 53 seconds
until family game night.
And about 5 minutes until I
put the moves on that amplifier.
Got to get out here...
You know, Murray. It occurs to me.
This concert's gonna add a lot
to my electricity bill.
You're right. How did I miss that?
Permission to dock my pay?
Don't worry about it.
I have an idea to recoup some cash!
Souvenir sales!
How about you start all the way
across the room,
then make your way
to the other side of the room,
avoiding this general vicinity?
Souvenirs! Get your bobbleheads here!
- [mic feedback]
- Hello, Richie Rich's bedroom!
[crowd whooping]
Thanks again, Richie.
Even though I can't see you,
because I can't turn my neck.
It means a lot
having you right by my side.
Yep. Right by your side.
That's where I'll be, all night.
Richie? Are you still there?
[Richie's voice]
Of course.
I'm right here, Darcy.
Do you think that amplifier
likes long walks on the beach?
Game night!
Time for some family bonding!
You're lucky I'm in a rush
to get this over with.
Otherwise I would take the time
to strangle you.
Okay, Harper's in the spirit.
This is all your fault.
I could be out doing something
fun with my Friday night,
like studying, if you hadn't
become Mr. Rich and Famous.
Okay, for the record,
I've been Mr. Rich since I was born.
Until last week, the name
was just tragically ironic.
Okay, time to play
Duck, Duck, Hippopotamus!
You mean "goose"?
I mean hippopotamus.
I couldn't find a goose costume.
- [both] Costume?
- Mm-hmm.
I thought the game would be more fun
if we all got into parts.
Maybe I will take the time
to strangle you.
- [muffled music]
- What's that booming noise?
Sounds like bass from a concert.
Concert? Ha... who has
a concert in their house?
That's... construction workers I
hired to hammer out the spackle.
[chuckles] Spackle.
So you guys ready to play?
Not really.
[cell phone "cha-ching" alert]
Uh-oh.
I'm not feeling too well.
I need a bathroom.
For everyone's sake, I'm gonna
use the one in the south wing.
[tires screeching]
Got your text. What's the emergency?
Your friend Darcy's very boring.
What?
You called me up here for that?
Well, that and Swedish House
Sensation keeps asking for you.
Is Richie Rich in ze house?
I would hope so, since it is his house.
Of course he's here!
He's right by my side.
Yep, been here all night.
Richie! Get up here and shake your rumpa!
This night's been a pain in my rumpa.
Incoming message from your sister:
[in Harper's voice]
"Richie, get back here!"
Okay, remember what I said
about my dad's voice
ruining the magic?
It's even more disturbing
when you use my sister's.
[all] Richie! Richie! Richie!
Murray! I need you to dance for me!
Put on my jacket and this mask
and make me look cool.
I can do two of those things.
[all] Richie! Richie!
Richie! Richie!
I'm back!
Richie, you're sweating.
You must really be sick.
We should cancel family game
night until he's all better.
And here's to hoping he doesn't
have one of those chronic
gastrointestinal disorders
that last a lifetime.
Maybe I should take you
to your room and put you to bed.
No! I mean...
you wouldn't be able to get in
because of that high-tech entry system.
And the eye scanner device.
Yeah, those are tricky.
All right, game on!
- [elevator bell dings]
- Duck... duck...
Hello! Richie?
My sister Gerta
has same hippopotamus costume.
- Who is that?
- Yeah, who is that?
Uh...
Gerta's brother?
What are you doing here?
You're supposed to be on stage.
I take bathroom break
and toilet chase me here.
Richie, what's going on here?
Who's the Swedish guy?
Sven.
Best meatball chef in the biz.
He adds a pinch of paprika
that really gives a bang to the ball.
Richie, I'm disappointed in you.
Dad, I can explain--
No, there's no excuse for this.
Everyone knows
the best meatballs are Italian.
You're right!
Sven, we better get you
and your paprika out of here.
Richie!
Who is paprika?
What is paprika?
[cha-ching]
[dance music playing]
♪ ♪
How's the music playing
if you're not even up there?
I am deejay.
I just hit button
and pretend to do stuff.
Well, get up there
and pretend to do stuff!
Ahh!
[thud]
Murray?
Irona, where's Richie?
[gasps]
Sleep mode.
I'm here!
[panting]
Why are you dressed
like Gerta House Sensation?
Good question. I'll go change.
Murray, there's something
going on with Richie.
We need to find him.
Grab the dolly!
Are you okay to push me?
I-I think so...
But I do need to make another appointment
with my chiropractor.
And my attorney.
[engine stuttering]
No! I can't be on empty!
Hello, Hallwayside Assistance?
Duck... duck...
Duck...
Hippopotamus!
Why aren't you chasing me?
- Self-pride.
- [elevator bell dings]
What are you two doing here?
Looking for Richie.
Hey, so are we!
Ooh, hide and seek.
I'm gonna go hide in my room
for the next ten years.
Hey, I'm back!
Richie, where have you been?
Yeah, where have you been?
Uh... sleep mode.
Dad, Richie was obviously
lying and sneaking off
to hang with his friends.
He needs to punished.
And if you need ideas, I have a list.
Richie, why'd you ditch me at the concert?
Concert? What concert?
Okay, here's the truth:
I promised I would take you guys
to Swedish House Sensation,
but then my dad
insisted on family game night.
I didn't want to let you guys
down so I moved the concert here
and tried to be in two places at once.
Richard Rich.
Are you telling me that
there are hundreds of strangers
at a concert in this house?
Do you know how much fun
Duck, Duck, Hippopotamus
would be with that many people?
Dad! What about Richie's punishment?
How 'bout number 37?
It's no food or water.
I'm sorry I wasn't honest with you guys.
I know you were worried
that we wouldn't be friends
- now that I'm rich and I didn't--
- Yeah, yeah.
Can we talk about this after the concert?
I really don't want
to miss 'Bout Them Meatballs.
I hate to give you credit, Richie...
[shrilly]
But this is awesome!
- Shh!
- I'm allowed to talk at a concert!
Tchotchkes! Get your tchotchkes here!
Check it! I'm breaking out the robot!
Oh, sure. Because all robots
move like that.
I am out of here.
Duck... duck... duck...
Duck...
Duck... duck...
Yeah, this turned out great.
Nothing's better than having fun
with the people I care about.
Wait... where's Darcy?
Guys?
You forgot someone!
Can anyone hear me?
[grunting]
Richie? Is that you?
[gorilla noises]
Uh-oh!