This is so sick!
- Knock-knock.
Whoa, amazing!
- It's a hovering surfboard--
all the fun of surfing
without any of the chafing
from a sand-filled bathing suit.
- No, what's amazing is,
I finally got that poppy seed
out of my teeth.
- Congrats, Dad.
If it's okay with you
and the poppy seed,
I'm gonna go back to surfing.
- Is there room up on that thing
for Sand Doggy?
I always wanted that
to be my nickname
in case I got into surfing.
- Sorry,
but this can't hold
both of us, Dad.
Sand Doggy.
- Live a little!
Here I come.
- I can't control this thing
with both of us on here!
- [crash]
- [grunts]
Oh, bummer.
- It's all right.
I can buy another one-of-a-kind
hovering surfboard.
My name is Richie Rich,
and I'm just a normal kid--
except that I have
a trillion dollars.
You see, I used
all the vegetables I never ate
to create a new energy source
and sold it
for a lot of money.
Now I live in a huge mansion
with my own amusement park,
race car,
and personal robot maid.
And I have my family and
the best friends in the world
to share my fortune with:
My dad,
my jealous sister, Harper,
my money manager, Murray,
and my money spender, Darcy.
I guess you could say,
by not eating my vegetables,
I became the richest
and luckiest kid in the world.
What are you doing?
- Redecorating...
my purse.
- Well, we have a problem.
Now that Richie 's
a trillionaire,
he could be a target
for criminals
after his money.
Other than you.
I think Richie needs
a security team.
They're not going to be, like,
checking people's bags
when they leave the house,
are they?
Maybe Richie doesn't need
a security team.
He's already throwing away
a lot of money
at unnecessary hangers-on.
Other than you.
Is there a point
to your babbling?
It occurs to me,
since you and I
are always by his side,
we would make
the perfect bodyguards.
Yes, criminals will surely
run and hide
after laying eyes
on your rippling rib bones.
- That is a medical condition.
- Called "scrawny."
- I'm aware
we'll require some training,
but we can hire
a tough military guy
to whip us into shape.
- Well, I'm in.
And I'm taking an advance
on my first paycheck.
- Hey, Harp.
Sand Doggy isn't in here,
is he?
- No.
Now run along.
Trying to have some fun.
- You're studying.
- [laughs]
This isn't homework.
I find grammatical errors
in textbooks for kicks.
Like right here?
Boom!
Dangling participle!
- What up, offspring?
I found
this awesome online quiz
called
"Which online quiz are you?"
I got "Which Hunger Games
sequel are you?"
It nailed me.
I am so that quiz.
- I'm kind of busy,
but Richie just mentioned
he had nothing to do, so...
- Not true, Harper.
I'm reading this textbook!
Boom!
Dangling something or other!
- So you guys
are doing homework, huh?
Boring!
[laughs]
- I am out of here.
The two of you have taken
all the joy
out of proofreading
this textbook.
- Come on, Harper.
Don't go.
So looks like
it's just you and me.
Want to go see
what your sister's doing?
- How 'bout we take that quiz?
- Yeah!
Now you're talking.
All right.
Okay.
Which planet best reflects
your personality?
Mars, Jupiter,
or Venus?
- Dad!
Fine, Venus.
- Are we done?
- Almost.
Only 49 more questions to go.
Now, what sound
do you find most soothing?
- The sound of your footsteps
leaving my room.
[remote beeps]
- What can I do for you,
Master Richie?
- Tell my dad which sound
you find most soothing.
[engine revving]
- I would have to say
the grinding of steel machinery
forging lug nuts out of
high-grade aluminum alloy.
- I don't see a box for that.
Do you have another...
[stammering]
Pretty.
- Do you have any more questions
for me, Mr. Rich?
- I, um...
pretty!
- Oh.
Hey, Murray.
I was thinking more
about that security thing,
and I think
it's a good idea.
- Good, because I found a guy
capable of transforming us
into top-notch bodyguards.
- A magician?
- No.
His name is Reaper,
and he's a martial arts
world champion,
decorated fighter pilot,
and hard-core
Special Forces commando.
- There are a lot of stairs
in this place.
I counted at least three
on my way from the elevator.
- Who are you?
- Reaper.
I'm here to...
[pants]
Train you.
- Sir, yes, sir!
- You're a martial arts expert
fighter pilot commando?
I was picturing someone
whose shirt
was covered in medals,
not cheese puff dust.
- I happen to hold
the high score
in six fighting games,
three flight simulators,
and seven first-person shooters.
- Those are video games!
Murray, get rid of this kid.
- I'm not messing with him.
This guy's a monster.
- Then I'm out of here.
- Do you want me to tell Richie
about that duffel bag
full of cash?
So what's our first exercise,
sensei?
- [sighs deeply]
Good.
- No Dad.
- Get lost.
- [yelps]
- This hiding spot's taken.
- We can't keep living
like this.
I love Dad, but I can't hang out
with him 24 hours a day.
- I can't believe these words
are coming out of my mouth,
but I agree with you.
I mean, I've tried to get him
interested in other things,
but nothing's worked.
- We need something
to occupy his time.
[gasps]
Like a job.
- Okay, let's be realistic.
How about a coloring book?
- What about a girlfriend?
Someone who could get him
out of the house
but also make him happy.
- Okay, Dad will never agree
to go on a date.
- We'll just trick him
into it,
like how we get him
to brush his teeth.
Okay, your plan works
in theory.
But where would we ever find
a woman desperate enough
to go out with him?
- The meeting place
of all things
lonely and desperate:
The Internet.
- Okay, Harper, let's fill out
Dad's dating profile.
I'll post Irona
at the door
to keep an eye out for him.
- According to my sensors,
he's currently in the pantry
banging on the door
trying to get out.
- Perfect.
I've filled out most of
the questions about Dad.
Now I just need to enter
his profession.
None.
And his interests.
[computer buzzes]
No matches found.
- The reason you didn't get
any matches
is because you were too honest.
This is the Internet.
Everything is fake.
According to my Wiki page,
I'm 6'2", dating Peyton List.
- You haven't checked it
recently, have you?
- Sand Doggy is moving.
He's in the elevator.
Okay, you have a second
because he just hit
all of the buttons.
Harper? Richie?
[stammering]
Pretty.
- Okay, I'm gonna give Dad
a new profile.
Profession: Bull rider/
astronaut / international spy.
- Richie, no one's ever going to
believe any of that.
- [computer dinging]
- Look!
Fake Dad got 79 matches.
- One problem.
These women are all beautiful,
and we both know
that Dad can't speak
around beautiful women.
Or beautiful robots.
- Aw.
I would be blushing
if I had
a cardiovascular system.
- Dad's a fun guy.
We'll find him
an unattractive woman
who he can be comfortable
around.
Too pretty.
Ooh, is that an unsightly mole
on her forehead?
- That is just dust
on the screen.
- Oh.
Then too pretty.
- What about this Aura woman?
She's hideous, and not only
did she list purple
as an interest,
but she misspelled it.
Perfect.
- There, I just set up
a date for tomorrow night.
Now what are you doing?
- Correcting my Wiki page.
"Mistreats his help"?
Harper,
why would you write that?
- Yes, Harper.
Why?
- Okay, you pigs.
It's fitness test time.
- This is humiliating.
I can't believe
I'm wearing a poly-cotton blend.
- No more squealing, honey!
- Understood, sir!
- In order to train you, I need
to know what I'm working with,
so do your best
to dodge these birds.
- Oh, I get it now.
You have us dressed up
in pig costumes because--
[grunts]
Man down.
- [laughs]
A man.
- Look alive!
You guys make me sick.
[groans]
Seriously, my stomach's
really queasy.
- [grunts]
- How is this supposed to
help us?
- Are you questioning
my methods?
- I am questioning
everything about you.
- All I ask of you
is patience.
Well, that and the deposit
for his pig suit.
I don't think I'm gonna
be able to return that.
- [yelps]
- There you are,
you sneaky little bugger.
- Actually, Dad,
I came in here
because we need to talk.
I'm having problems at school.
- [laughs]
Don't sweat it.
I never did great in school,
and look how I turned out.
Well, my teacher
is sweating it,
so much so she's coming
over here right now
to have an emergency
parent-teacher conference.
- Right now?
But I had plans.
I was gonna play with you.
- I'm sorry, Dad.
School comes before play.
Now, I need you to impress her.
Go put on a suit and tie.
- I don't own a suit.
Unless you count my bear suit.
[doorbell dings]
- Oh, that must be her.
I need you to go put on
a suit I got you.
It's in your closet
next to your fireman costume.
- So far, so good.
Now, time to meet Dad's date.
Bring in the creature!
- Hi.
I'm Aura.
You're not hideous at all!
- Uh...
thank you?
- This is very disappointing.
You're the one person
who's actually prettier
than your online picture.
- [laughing]
Guilty!
I do that to weed out
superficial men only into looks.
- [scoffs]
Is there another kind?
- Excuse us.
What'll we do?
She's gorgeous, and it's
too late to bail on the plan.
- Is Cliff here,
or did he get called away
on a last-minute spy mission?
- Spy mission?
Oh, right, because he's a spy.
Well, I'm afraid
that's classified.
- Would you mind
telling your dad I'm here?
- Dad?
Agent Cliff doesn't have
any children.
He comes with no baggage
of any kind.
- I'm not his son.
I'm his CIA handler.
I'm actually a bit of a prodigy.
[chuckles]
- That's right,
and I am--
- The help.
- What?
[chuckles]
I'm a little too qualified to--
- Yeah, yeah, yeah,
you're way too good
for the job you begged for.
Now run along
and fetch Aura a beverage.
I will not.
- If you want Dad to like her,
get her a drink
and spill it on her.
Make her ugly.
I'm a prodigy
at handling spies,
but handling house hands,
not my thing.
[chuckles]
Now, because you don't have
secret clearance,
if you mention anything
about spying,
Agent Cliff will act like
he doesn't have a clue.
- Got it.
- Actually,
no matter the subject,
there's a good chance
he'll act like
he doesn't have a clue.
- Oh.
[gasps]
- Harper!
To your maid quarters
to think about what you've done.
I apologize for her.
There.
You look perfect.
- Hey, I'm Cliff.
I'd like to apologize for--
- Harper?
I know.
I've already apologized.
- How about we go to the meal?
- Meal?
I didn't know
we were gonna eat.
It's been a while
since I've done one of these.
- [chuckles]
Your dinner awaits.
Wow.
For someone so rusty,
you sure know
what you're doing.
- Thanks.
- [laughs]
- No one's ever said that
to me before.
- Oh.
- I don't know about you two,
but I'm seeing fireworks...
right out there.
- I can't believe you did
all that for me.
- [chuckles]
Neither can I.
- Well, get out there, kids,
and enjoy your 12-course meal.
- I don't think
Aura wants to spend
any more time than she has to.
- Oh, come on.
I've been looking forward
to this.
- That can't be good.
- I'm in serious trouble.
That's why I bought this.
- Thanks.
But I don't look good
in necklaces.
Ow!
- Well, in that case,
maybe you should give it
to her.
Oh.
- Come on, you guys.
I need more height
in those sit-ups.
Cheese.
Salsa.
Is that all you guys got?
- Unless you plan on
licking the bowl,
which I imagine you are.
- Way to work those abs.
Okay, let's move on
to some martial arts.
I'm gonna arm you
with the most specialized moves
in existence.
- I have some karate experience.
I signed up when I heard about
the free belts,
but I was done-zo
when I found out
they weren't snakeskin.
- I may have to sit this out
as I am currently dealing
with a serious
medical condition.
- Called "scrawny."
- [sighs]
Don't worry.
Neither of you will actually
have to do anything.
- That I can handle.
- You're gonna learn these moves
through muscle memory.
I will control your bodies
with my controllers.
- How's that going to work?
- Electro-stimulus bodysuits.
They send the signals
from my controllers
directly to your muscles,
turning you into
real, live video game
characters.
- Ooh, can I be
the interest rate slasher?
That's this awesome character
that pops up on my banking app.
- Listen, Reaper, there's no way
these things actually work.
Whoa!
- Stop. Stop!
- Are you hurt?
- Worse.
I'm sweating.
- Actually, so am I.
Pause.
- Whoa.
How'd he do that?
- Lose his breath
tapping a controller?
I have no idea.
- Okay, stop.
- We can't.
You're controlling us.
- No, I'm not.
- Then how are we doing things
like this?
- Muscle memory.
I'm over here playing
Persian Empire Invasion,
and it's really got me
craving falafel.
- So we can actually do
all the things
our bodies just did?
- Yep.
My work here is done.
Well, it will be
once I get down those stairs.
[sighs deeply]
- Murray,
I got to give you credit.
I doubted you,
but this whole plan of yours
actually worked.
You're a smart guy.
- Nice try, but I'm obligated
to tell Richie
about the duffel bag.
- I understand.
- Darcy!
- I can't believe
Dad and Aura
are actually hitting it off.
- I believe it.
Did you see the size
of that diamond
I gave him to give her?
[both laughing]
- You know,
I didn't expect to have
this much fun with you tonight.
I just expected
a typical guy
blabbing about his job.
[laughing]
- It'd be impossible for me
to talk about my job.
Aura, you're amazing.
And I wanted to know
if you would like to go out
with me tomorrow.
- I'd love to.
By the way, I never asked you:
What problems are you having
with Richie in class?
- Richie?
[both] Uh-oh.
- Okay, Dad--
I mean, Cliff.
Tell Aura you'll see her
tomorrow.
- Have fun on your date!
[quietly]
Don't wear makeup.
- Hold on,
you're not really
a CIA handling prodigy,
are you?
- I'm not at liberty
to confirm or deny that.
- Prodigy?
He's barely passing your class.
- What class?
- Okay, the truth is--
- Richie set you up on a date,
and I told him not to,
but he totally did it.
- Someone tell me
what's going on.
- Dad, Harper and I
set you guys up on a date
because we needed some space.
- I mean,
we love to spend time with you,
but we do need time to ourselves
occasionally.
- You're an amazing dad,
and you deserve someone
other than us in your life
who sees how much fun you are.
- That is one of the sweetest
things I've ever heard.
Cliff,
you must be a great man,
because you raised
one great kid.
- Hello.
[chuckles]
I'm great, too.
- Thanks, guys.
I guess I could give you
a little more space.
Aura, still want to
go out on that date?
- I'd love to.
[laughs]
Richie, thanks for
introducing me to your dad,
even if it was
in an incredibly devious way.
[laughs]
Come here, you.
- Richie's under attack!
- Get her!
[both grunt]
[thudding]
- Okay, okay, okay.
Darcy, Murray, stop.
- [exhales]
Threat neutralized.
- She isn't a threat.
- Not anymore.
You owe me one...
thousand dollars.
I'll go help myself.
- Aura.
- Are you okay?
- No.
You know, I could tell
you were all crazy people
the second I walked in,
but I figured
the chance of marrying
into this much money
was worth a shot.
It's not.
Well, looks like
it's just us three again.
Want to play?
How 'bout spies?
[as Sean Connery ]
I think Agent Cliff
is a great spy name, huh?
- Good idea!
Okay, Agent Cliff.
Orders from base.
Foreign agents
are searching for you,
and you need to go
into hiding.
- Got it.
They'll never find me.
Should we get him?
- Nah.