Whoo!
♪ Love in an elevator ♪
No, wrong song.
♪ sweet ♪
♪ emotion ♪
♪ I talk about people ♪
♪ that can't really sing ♪
♪ dah dah dah dah dah ♪
♪ bah dah dah dah dah ♪
♪ and when they get ♪
♪ the confidence of what ♪
♪ they're gonna bring ♪
♪ doo dohn dohn ♪
♪ dah dah dah ♪
Edit.
Welcome to Milwaukee, Wisconsin.
♪ Sweet ♪
It's our very first time
visiting this city, and the
people were proud to tell
us what they're all about.
We don't have an accent here.
We just like our cheese and beer.
Yeah!
But they also love their hometown
hero, season eight's Danny gokey.
Are you excited to try out?
Yeah.
Yeah?
This was me two years ago.
I was just in a line amongst
thousands of people.
Anything could happen.
From this moment, your life can
completely change, you guys.
It really can.
♪
But first, they'll have
to get past these three.
♪ Milwaukee ♪
Looking forward to seeing
who we find out here.
♪
♪ sweet ♪
We're trying to find a
complete package, right?
That's the goal, the package.
♪ Emotion ♪
A little breath of fresh air.
Yes.
Slap that baby on the ass
and call me Christmas.
What?
Milwaukee, let's be about it.
♪ Sweet emotion ♪
And our panel will conduct their search
at the renowned Milwaukee art museum.
♪
This is exciting.
Amazing view out here.
The lake.
Let's get this crackin'.
Let's get it rollin'.
The judges have taken their seats...
♪ let's get this started ♪
♪ yeah ♪
And across town, the stadium
is filled and ready to roll.
Let's hope the next American
idol comes out of Milwaukee!
Danny already put his city on
the map, but who will be next?
Today, there are people
auditioning from all around the
country, ready to represent
for their hometown.
I'm from cedar falls, Iowa.
I'm from salt lake city, Utah.
I'm from San Jose, California.
I'm from wauwatosa, Wisconsin.
Martin, Kentucky.
Gary, Indiana.
Oak forest, Illinois.
♪ Mmm ♪
But the first contender of the day
comes from a place far from Milwaukee.
He's the pride of
garner, north Carolina.
Meet Scotty mccreary.
Growing up in garner has
been a great experience.
You know, a lot of the high
school kids, they say, "oh, I
can't wait to go to college and
get out of here," but I tell
'em, "look, this is a great
town to grow up in."
A lot of people would describe
me as an all-American kid, you
know, playing baseball
my whole life.
Atta boy.
Scotty's a great kid.
He's the role model on the team.
He's been one of our better pitchers,
you know, coming up through the ranks.
If Scotty were to make it through,
I think garner would erupt.
It'd be too cool to get that
golden ticket and, uh, to bring
it back home to garner.
What's your name?
Scott mccreary. Scotty.
Oh, Scott.
Scotty mccreary, sir.
How are you?
How old are you, Scott?
16 years old.
I'm doing good.
You're 16?
Young man.
You have a deep voice.
I get that a lot.
Thank you, thank you.
"I get that a lot."
So tell us a little
bit about yourself.
I've been singing country
music my whole life.
I love to do it, and I hope
y'all like country music.
I hope you can sing.
I started singing at one.
The doctor told me I hummed a
few lines of bye, baby bunting.
Was a little nursery rhyme my mom sang
to me when I was in the cradle, I guess.
How does it go?
♪ Bye, baby bunting ♪
That's all I did, I think, but...
Jennifer's got babies, so
that's why I was, like,
just giving her some stuff.
All right, well, what are
you gonna sing today?
Your man by Josh Turner.
Okay.
♪ Baby, lock them doors ♪
♪ and turn the lights down low ♪
♪ put some music on ♪
♪ that's soft and slow ♪
♪ and baby, we ain't got ♪
♪ no place to go ♪
♪ and I hope you understand ♪
♪ well, I've been thinkin' ♪
♪ 'bout this all day long ♪
♪ never felt a feeling ♪
♪ quite this strong ♪
♪ and I can't believe ♪
♪ how much it turns me on ♪
♪ just to be your man ♪
Wow.
You made me smile.
Yeah.
I guess that's good.
I like you, man, I like you.
You made me smile.
Guy, can you sing something else
that... that's... that's... higher?
Yeah, a little, you know, that...
that... that spans the test of time.
Okay, I can sing some
Travis tritt for you.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think you, uh, produced
some songs with Travis.
I produced an album with Travis.
What are you gonna sing?
Put some drive in your country.
All right, do it, do it.
♪ Well, I was raised ♪
♪ on country classics ♪
♪ like Roy acuff ♪
♪ and George Jones ♪
♪ and lord ♪
♪ I loved to hear 'em ♪
♪ sing all them ♪
♪ old-time country songs ♪
♪ well, I really got excited ♪
♪ 'bout the time I turned 15 ♪
♪ well, that's the first time ♪
♪ I heard waylon ♪
♪ and old bocephus sing ♪
♪ they put some drive ♪
♪ in their country ♪
♪ that really turned men ♪
Well, hellfire, save matches, [bleep]
a duck and see what hatches.
What are we doing in here?
Yo, man!
Yo! Yo!
Aren't I allowed to say that?
Yo! What is going on?
Whoo!
We'll loop it later and
we'll say "suck a duck."
This is a young man who's 16.
But it ain't nothin' I ain't
heard in high school, brother.
It ain't nothin' I ain't
heard in high school.
You sing... that... that's...
that's beautiful.
Thank you very much.
I agree, I agree.
Thank you.
Uh, yeah.
I can see a new artist there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right, so,
Steven, you say yes?
I say yes.
Jennifer?
Thank you.
Dude, love you.
Love that you're a throwback country
guy, singing low like that.
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
The Randy Travis, all in.
Dude, I love it, dude.
I love it.
Very well done.
Welcome to Hollywood!
Yeah!
Thank you very much.
You're legendary.
Wow.
Thank you.
Dude, and at 16?
I'm so impressed, man.
16.
There's promise for America yet.
And you know why you
can go and kill me?
'Cause he came on without his hat.
Exactly, exactly.
Thank you all very much.
Thank you.
He's the new country.
Yep.
I did it.
So garner's hometown boy did good.
With the right songs,
we discovered him.
Oh, no, he... he's on his way.
This kid... this kid is
in for a long career.
With the right songs, whoo!
Whoo!
We have much more from Milwaukee
coming up after the break.
It's freezing.
Awesome.
Steven Tyler, you are insane.
You are insane, brother.
Over the next two hours,
the insanity escalates.
♪ Aah ♪
♪ aah ♪
♪ aaaaahhh ♪
And the stars in
Milwaukee shine bright.
Dude, you were hot.
Outstanding.
Wow!
Whoo-hoo!
But later... I want this so bad.
Wisconsin wanders
to the dark side.
Oh, no.
Put the gun down.
That's gonna be me right now.
The heartless woman.
Aah!
You all right?
♪
♪ oh, oh ♪
It's 10 A.M. at the Milwaukee
art museum, and so far, the
auditions are off
to a strong start.
How's everybody feeling today?
Is everybody good?
This is great!
I feel... I feel like I'm
on a jungle gym here.
It's great.
Yay, idol crew!
♪ Never stop for a minute ♪
But it's not just the
judges who are pumped.
So far this morning, the entire
city has been buzzing about idol.
Our big story this morning, are
you the next American idol?
It's happened.
American idol is in Milwaukee.
Well, take a look here as,
uh, thousands of people now
entering the Bradley
center, screaming.
They're excited.
But perhaps no one was more
excited than one Joe repka.
I'm gonna kick this thing
straight to the moon.
♪
And I have a feeling we're
gonna get along just fine.
Joe?
Yes, Joe.
Joe, what do you do?
Uh, I'm a student at ut.
Excellent.
What are you studying?
Uh, communications.
I want to try and get into radio.
I love radio.
I know.
You're on radio.
Reach to the beats that's rockin' the
docks, runnin' late and soundin' great.
Remember, you can pick your
friends, you can pick your nose,
but you can't wipe your
friends on the couch.
I know what you're saying, man.
So I took this future deejay under my
wing and put him through his paces.
Top of the hour, top of the hour.
This is wkko, Toledo.
Top, big number... top of the hour.
Again.
This is big Joe repka, coming
at you live on Toledo's k100.
K100.
Toledo's k100.
Yeah, I have a habit
of doing that a lot.
So in theory, you could be playing
your own song on the air.
That's... that's the
perfect scenario.
That's a possi... that's
a possibility, yeah.
♪
Good deal.
Nice to meet a, uh, budding
radio personality.
Yeah.
It's nice to meet... meet a
current radio personality.
Thank you.
It's good to be here.
When I get in there, I'm kind of most
excited to see the lovely miss Jennifer.
I mean...
Yeah!
Wow, are those tevas?
Hmm?
Uh... huh?
I don't know exactly
what brand they are.
They're just some old brand I had.
Nice.
Thank you.
I like, I like.
So, listen, what's your name?
Uh, my name is Joe repka.
Joe repka.
And how old are you, Joe?
I'm 19.
From?
I'm from swanton, Ohio.
And what do you do?
Uh, I'm a student right now
at the university of Toledo,
studying communications.
I want to get on radio.
Is that like, uh, our friend Mr. Seacrest?
Yeah, like... like Mr.
Seacrest, deejaying
it all up, you know?
You got a good radio voice?
Yeah, I... I hope so.
Let's hear a little bit.
Let's hear something.
This is big Joe repka coming at you
loud and proud on Toledo's k100.
That... was that the mic?
The mic.
The mic in and out.
Tsst, tsst.
How do you imagine that
seacrest does his?
Honestly, I'm sorry to say, I don't
listen to him all that much.
What?
I'm more of a country man.
I listen to country music a lot.
I know what happens.
You tune in to Ryan if you must.
If there's nothing else on.
Exactly.
Okay.
Randy, come on, you're
killing me here.
Okay.
Don't... don't... don't...
don't put it like that.
No.
All right.
Singing is your dream?
Yes.
You are, without a doubt, the
next American idol, right?
Well, I hope so.
All right, what are
you gonna sing?
The longest time by Billy Joel.
Great song.
Okay.
Did he sing in the car on
the way over, to rehearse?
Oh, he sings everywhere.
He does?
Wherever we go.
Yeah, he sings all the time.
Ah, that's cool.
Do you sing?
No.
I'm tone deaf.
One, two, three, four.
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ for the longest ♪
♪ if you said good-bye ♪
♪ to me tonight ♪
♪ there would still be ♪
♪ music left to write ♪
♪ that's when you found me ♪
♪ when you wrapped your arms ♪
♪ around me ♪
♪ I haven't been there ♪
♪ for the longest time ♪
Wow. All right, dude.
All right.
Wow.
Brutally honest.
Yes, Steven.
Are you ready?
Yes.
'Cause you came here
to hear it, right?
Yes.
Do not quit your day job.
Don't sing into the mic.
Talk into it.
Okay.
'Cause I like that voice
better than this one.
All right.
Wow.
I-I think you could have, uh,
the thing with the mic and the
whole thing could be really fun for
you, and you should pursue that.
Okay.
I, too, agree with my
fellow cohorts here.
Dude, definitely radio.
No to singing.
Definitely the deejay thing.
♪ Wise men say ♪
♪ Only fools rush in ♪
This is weird.
Weren't we talking?
♪ But I can't help ♪
Did we even comment?
I don't think he heard us.
♪ Falling in love with you ♪
That was a beautiful duet with you
and Steven, though, I must admit.
You guys maybe could
form a different band.
We can.
The rubber band.
Yeah.
Snap.
Steven, yes?
No.
Jennifer, yes?
Randy, yes?
No.
It's three nos, Joe.
All right.
But we had a good
time with you, man.
Thank you.
Take care.
You too.
We'll be listening for
you on the radio.
All right.
Ryan, he's gonna take your spot.
Take care.
♪
Nah.
That's too bad, sweeTheart.
How do you feel about it?
Ah, I did all right.
Of course, they were brutally honest
with me, and I appreciate that.
Steven said, "don't
quit the day job."
But, you know, I'll
stay in school.
I promise you, I'm
gonna try again.
In the meantime...
Yeah, still the deejaying.
On Toledo's k100.
I like that.
So even though Joe won't be
performing on our stage, you
might just be hearing him
on your morning commute.
Good morning, everyone.
This is big Joe repka,
taking you to work.
And now, here is some more of
your big hits, starting off with
Carrie Underwood.
For 15-year-old Emma Henry, driving to
the auditions has been a lifelong dream.
As soon as my family found out
that they lowered the age to
15, we basically loaded up the
car and we drove 16 hours from
Littleton, Colorado, to
Milwaukee, Wisconsin.
♪ While we're young ♪
♪ and beautiful ♪
Take it easy, Emma.
We're over the speed limit.
I remember the speed limit.
I just got my permit, so
I drove most of the way.
Hands on the wheel!
Sorry.
The drive was just, like, symbolic, just
driving on my way to my opportunity.
♪ And beautiful ♪
I've been watching the show
ever since Kelly clarkson won.
I think I was five years old.
The winner of American idol is...
Kelly clarkson.
That moment, I've always just...
I've wanted that so bad.
Music is basically my life.
This is my dream.
This is all that I want.
Hello.
Hi.
What's your name?
My name's Emma.
Hi, Emma.
How old are you, Emma?
I'm 15.
What are you singing today?
I'm gonna sing true
colors by cyndi Lauper.
Nice.
Do it.
Okay.
♪ You with the sad eyes ♪
♪ don't be discouraged ♪
♪ though I realize ♪
♪ it's hard to take courage ♪
♪ in a world full of people ♪
♪ you can lose sight of it all ♪
♪ and the darkness ♪
♪ goes inside you ♪
♪ makes you feel so small ♪
♪ but I see your true colors ♪
♪ shining through ♪
♪ I see your true colors ♪
♪ and that's why I love you ♪
♪ so don't be afraid ♪
♪ to let them show ♪
♪ your true colors ♪
♪ are beautiful ♪
♪ like a rainbow ♪
I loved it.
You got... you got a certain something
I can't put my finger on right now.
Yeah.
But it's got a lot of character.
Good, good.
And that's what I liked.
Cool.
There is, there's something
there for you to build on.
But you have a special quality,
and so, you should... you should
keep working on that, working on
that, because that's what great
recording artists are made of.
They have a quality
in their voice.
They have a special tone
that nobody else has.
Okay.
I'm not sure I think
that you're ready yet.
Oh, please.
But, uh, let's take a
vote and see where we go.
Okay.
Um, I'm gonna say
no for right now.
I think you need to work on it a
little bit before you get into
something as big as this, okay?
Steven?
I liked you.
I'm gonna say yes.
Thank you.
Please.
This is... I want this so bad.
This is what my life is about.
Well, this is just the
beginning, right?
And you're 15.
I'm 15, but... so you've got a
whole life of music ahead of you.
I don't want to go home now.
I've tried so hard.
Hmm.
Well, listen, I really, really,
honestly believe you'll get
swallowed up in this whole thing.
Oh, no, I won't.
This is the best talent show ever.
We tell a lot of people, "you're
terrible, get out of here.
What are you doing?
What's going on?"
But you actually have some skill.
You just need to work on it a
little bit more and develop it.
Oh, my God.
I hear crying too.
I just wish she wasn't sick.
Is she sick?
Yeah, she's had a bad cold.
I think she... she
looked frustrated.
Dog's gonna turn into
a pussycat right now.
Come on, dog.
Come on.
I mean, if you didn't hear
something there, I mean...
I-I am gonna work so hard.
Guess what.
You got another shot.
Yes!
Thank you!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Thank you, thank you!
You get one more shot.
Don't disappoint us.
No.
And you know what?
On the ride home... yeah?
Try... belt it out a
little bit more.
Okay.
Go... ♪ la dah Dee ♪
♪ la dah ♪
♪ yahhh ♪
Okay.
'Cause it was just...
it was all here.
It needs to... it can go
these places, right?
More energy, come on.
Thank you, guys.
♪ I feel like I once... ♪
Yeah, 'cause I was fighting them.
You were pushing them.
Yes!
Your... your first
instinct was right.
She's gonna get eaten
up in this competition.
My thing was... you have your learner's
permit and a ticket to Hollywood.
Yes!
Good.
I'm set.
You're set.
Congratulations.
We'll see you there.
And we'll see you
right after this.
Coming up, emotions run
high in Milwaukee.
People ask a lot of time,
like, "why are you crying?
Why are you crying?"
'Cause it means a lot.
But the talent level
is even higher.
She's so good.
I love this girl,
I love this girl.
Voice-wise, one of
the best we've seen.
Outstanding.
As the midwest heats up, everybody
is ready for their shot.
Let's just talk!
Don't try me, man!
Aaah!
Welcome back to Wisconsin...
Where so far today, we've discovered
some fantastic new talent.
Waiting outside in the holding
room are several others ready to
get in on the action.
Each one of them realizes that
their shot at Hollywood is just
a few short steps away.
Well, hello there.
Hi.
Hello.
I love your getup.
How would you describe your voice?
Kind of a little bluesy.
Mmm!
Like, what artist would you say?
Frank Sinatra.
Oh, nice.
Wide range.
So, have you been singing
for a long time?
As long as I can remember.
Show us everything you got.
All right.
♪ Rah rah, rah ah ah ♪
♪ rumma rum mah mah ♪
♪ gaga, ooh la la ♪
♪ want your bad romance ♪
♪ it's true ♪
♪ we're all a little insane ♪
♪ I'm your biggest fan ♪
♪ I'll follow you ♪
♪ until you love me ♪
♪ papa, paparazzi ♪
♪ You and me together ♪
♪ through the days and nights ♪
♪ I don't worry 'cause ♪
♪ everything's gonna be ♪
♪ all right ♪
Wow.
That was terrible.
Frank Sinatra, huh?
Where was Frank in that?
Maybe that was a bad comparison.
Dude, it was terrible.
What was terrible?
Pitch, tone, sound,
everything about singing.
I gotta pass. No.
Oh.
It's just not gonna happen today.
Okay.
No.
Really?
Never.
If gaga were here, she'd run out of the
room screaming, "what have I done?
Aah!"
Thanks.
He didn't like that.
Can I give you a hug?
You better.
Okay.
Dude.
Can I have a sip of your coke?
Uh, no.
Okay.
Just... I... it's coke zero.
I mean, you can get
some out there, yeah.
All right, well,
thank you very much.
Okay.
Look at him.
Wow.
As the afternoon grows on,
finding talent here is quickly
turning into a losing battle,
which is surprising, 'cause
Milwaukee is home to the biggest music
festival in the world...
Summerfest.
The event has even hosted some
of our own idol stars along the
way, so it's no surprise that
one of this year's contestants,
naema aridapo, also has a
connection to this place, but
not in the way you might think.
Life is kind of crazy for me
because I am an artist, but I
work a 9:00 to 5:00 with
summerfest, and basically, it's
like grounds cleanup, you
know, janitorial stuff.
I'm, like, cleaning
this huge amphiTheatre.
It's, like, thousands of people.
And I'm looking at the stage,
and I'm like, "that should be
me," but instead I'm behind the
stage, cleaning the toilets and
making sure everything is tidy.
I decided to audition this year
because really, honestly, I feel
like it would change my life.
If I could provide for my family
and give to my daughters what I
didn't have, it would be a
great change for us, and so...
It's real.
People ask... I'm sorry, I'm
gonna start to cry, baby.
But, um, peoplask a lot of time,
like, "why are you crying?
Why are you crying?"
'Cause it means a lot.
But, you know, I just pray
that it goes, um, well.
And I feel like it will, so...
Hello, hello.
Hi.
How are you?
Nice colors, man.
Thank you.
Yeah, you know, I need it.
What's your name?
Naema, naema aridapo.
What do you like to sing?
Who's your favorite artist?
What I was gonna sing for you
today is, um, a Donny hathaway
song, for all we know.
Mmm!
Okay.
Do it.
Let's hear it.
♪ For all we know ♪
♪ this may only be a dream ♪
♪ we come and we go ♪
♪ like the ripples ♪
♪ of a stream ♪
♪ so love me ♪
♪ love me tonight ♪
♪ tomorrow was made for some ♪
Okay.
I like you a lot.
I think she's, voice-wise and
the whole package-wise, one of
the best we've seen.
Very nice.
What do you think, Randy?
I like her.
I like her a lot.
Me too.
Thank you.
Ditto.
I think you're all that.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Thank you.
You're all that too.
Yeah.
I got no love, I got no love?
I get no love over here?
Hey, say it to Jennifer.
No love, right?
No.
I get a vote too.
Steve, you want to go first?
Steven.
Stevie?
Whoa, whoa.
Naema, that was great.
Thank you.
I say yes.
Randy?
Randy Jackson.
What the hell?
Why'd he say that?
He's Steve.
He said, "Steven."
Okay, yeah.
Uh, yes, 100% yes.
I love this girl.
It's a yes.
You're going to Hollywood.
Welcome to Hollywood!
Whoa, baby!
Whoa!
Welcome to Hollywood!
Yes.
Wow.
I keep calling you Steve
and it's Steven, right?
You could call me late for
dinner, and I'd still love you.
But not lunch.
Don't call me late
for no... not us.
Mm-mm, not the kid, mm-mm.
Hey, now, Randy Jackson.
Mr. Jackson, if you're nasty...
Randy dean... no, Randy dean
Jackson, my whole name.
Don't call me at all, both of you.
Wow.
But don't refer to
me as "hey, you."
We'll be back after this.
Stay with us.
After the break, you will not
believe the talent in Milwaukee.
All the isms are jumping off.
None of the wasums.
Beautiful.
Including our youngest
contestants ever.
And everyone wants to get in on
the party, including Randy, who
comes fist to face
with a contestant.
Oh, hi, welcome to American idol.
Jennifer Lopez.
We don't speak on the set.
No?
We don't speak.
By the way, you and
your ways, all right?
You and your ways.
Let's do it.
He's such a diva and
I can't take it.
It's 2:00 P.M. in Milwaukee,
and we're back from break, but
in the holding room, the
party hasn't stopped.
Here we go, here
we go, here we go!
Oh, yeah!
It's all fun and games
until someone gets hurt.
Are you all right?
Not to be cruel, but
let's see that again.
♪
Back inside, things weren't
turning out any better.
Day one in Milwaukee, and for
the last couple of hours,
there's been a dry spell
in the audition room.
♪ Don't be fooled ♪
♪ by the rocks that I got ♪
♪ I'm still, I'm still ♪
♪ Jenny from the block ♪
♪ I used to have a little ♪
♪ now I've got a lot ♪
♪ it doesn't matter ♪
♪ where I know where ♪
♪ I come from ♪
That's gonna be me right now.
The heartless woman.
Uh-oh.
Mmm!
♪
Hi.
Uh-oh.
♪ Oh, you better ♪
♪ get out the brush ♪
♪ everybody ♪
Sing in your car only.
With the windows up.
Perhaps bar mitzvah singer Jerome bell
will be just what the doctor ordered.
Here we go.
Let's do it.
Energy!
Hi!
How are y'all doing?
Good. How are you?
What's going on, Jerome bell?
How are you doin',
how are you doin'?
What's going on, bell?
Not a whole lot.
You know, just trying to
make it to Hollywood.
I love your sneakers.
Thank you.
I call them my space boots.
Nice.
Yeah.
What do you do?
Uh, I sing at bar
mitzvahs and weddings.
Really?
Okay.
Are you a performer?
No.
Oh, come on.
I think there's a
little star in there.
No, I only sing for little people.
That's me.
What are you singing today?
Uh, I'm gonna sing a little bit of,
um, let's get it on by Marvin gaye.
Do it, baby.
Nice.
All right.
♪ I've been really tryin' ♪
♪ baby ♪
♪ tryin' to hold back ♪
♪ this feelin' ♪
♪ for so long ♪
♪ and if you feel ♪
♪ like I feel, baby ♪
♪ then come on ♪
♪ oh, come on ♪
♪ whoo ♪
♪ let's get it on ♪
♪ yeah, baby ♪
♪ let's love, baby ♪
♪ I said, let's get it on ♪
♪ sugar ♪
♪ let's get it on ♪
♪ ooh ooh ♪
All right, cool.
Ha!
That's what we like.
People that can sing
to be up in here.
Oh!
Bam!
With space boots on.
Yeah.
Hot, crazy vocals.
In tune, controlled.
Tender the right moments.
Nice dynamics.
All over the... yeah.
I like you, man.
I like you.
What do you think, Jennifer?
Loud, soft, sweet.
I know, got all
of... all the stuff.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Cute.
Outstanding.
Thank you.
All the isms jumping off.
Yeah.
Steven?
None of the wasums.
Beautiful.
Good to hear, good to
hear, good to hear.
So good, so good.
Wow.
I think we should... yeah.
We should just vote right away.
I'm gonna say yes.
Yes.
You're going to Hollywood!
Whoo!
Yes, that's the way to do it.
Wow.
We look forward to
seeing you over there.
That's the way to come
in and nail an audition.
Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
No complaining.
Yeah! Whoo!
♪ Baby ♪
♪ everything is all right ♪
♪ uptight and out of sight ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ everything is all right ♪
Whoo!
♪ Whoo ♪
Yeah, that was good.
What was... what was his name?
Jerome bell.
Where are we?
Page four.
Remember that name.
We'll see if Jerome has what
it takes to make it to our big
stage, a place that has
showcased some of the biggest
names in music,
including this guy.
♪ Baby, baby, baby, oh ♪
♪ like, baby, baby, baby ♪
And unless you've been living
under a rock, you know bieber
fever is still running
rampant across the country.
♪ You'd always be mine ♪
♪ mine ♪
So it got us thinking.
Because of his staggering
success at such a young age,
perhaps we should lower the age
limit for our contestants.
♪ Girl ♪
♪ put your records on ♪
♪ tell me your favorite song ♪
♪ just go ahead ♪
♪ let your hair down ♪
Yay!
Wow! Wow!
Well, maybe not that low.
But we did lower the age limit
to 15, and they've certainly
delivered so far on the road.
But they're going to have some
serious competition to contend
with here in Milwaukee.
My name is Thea magea.
I am 15 years old, and I'm from
mountain house, California, and
I'm a high school student.
I originally planned on
auditioning next year for season
11, but when I heard about
the age reduction, I just
immediately booked flights and a hotel
and we just flew straight to Wisconsin.
Um, I knew that there was gonna
be auditions in California, but
I just couldn't summon
the patience to wait.
Thea magea.
It kind of rhymes.
I like that.
Is that your real name?
Yeah.
Okay, just checking.
That's a... that's a
movie star name.
It sure is.
Thank you.
How old are you?
I'm 15 years old.
So you're here auditioning.
What's the... what's the story?
What's the dream?
You've been wanting to do this all
your life, even though you're only 15?
Yeah, I mean, I've been
watching this show since season
one, and I just can't
believe I'm here right now.
I'm actually really
star-struck to see you guys.
I mean, Randy, I've been seeing
you on television even before I
could even start reading, so...
Whoa.
I'm here now.
But I'm still mad
young, though, right?
You look exactly the same.
Exactly, exactly.
Doesn't he look exactly the
same as in season one?
You look even younger.
Younger.
Even younger.
I love this girl.
This girl knows what's going on.
Okay, so, uh, what are
you singing today?
Uh, chasing pavements by Adele.
Great song.
Do it, do it.
Have fun with it, okay?
♪ Should I give up ♪
♪ or should I just ♪
♪ keep chasing pavements ♪
♪ even if it leads nowhere? ♪
♪ or would it be a waste ♪
♪ even if I knew my place ♪
♪ should I leave it there? ♪
♪ should I give up ♪
♪ or should I just ♪
♪ keep chasing pavements ♪
♪ even if it leads nowhere? ♪
♪ yeah ♪
Nice.
All right, thanks, Thea.
Let's see what the
panel thinks, man.
What do you think, Jennifer?
I love you.
I think you're the total package.
Mmm.
And you're very
comfortable up there.
Thank you.
Steven?
I loved your voice.
Thank you.
I thought it had a lot of
character and all of that muster
and smoke and heat,
you know, down there.
You know, it would have been a place
that, you know... Steven Tyler.
I'm just saying.
Legend.
I-I like you a lot.
Let's take a vote here.
Steven?
Thea, I say yes.
Jennifer?
I say yes too.
I say yes.
You've got three yeses.
Welcome to Hollywood!
Whoo!
But it wasn't just Thea.
By 4:00, it was clear our
decision had paid off.
Every 15-year-old who walked
in walked out with gold.
Nice.
That's beautiful.
I think you've got a really
strong, interesting voice.
You're 15.
I say yes.
Yay!
And a yes from me.
♪ Yes ♪
You're through to Hollywood.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Welcome.
15 and she could do that?
Wow.
See, this is why the winners
come from these places.
I mean, it's like, one
person after the other.
And it was smooth
sailing in Milwaukee.
It feels so good to have
some people that can sing.
What could possibly go wrong?
♪ aaaaaaah ♪
No!
Half of these people cannot sing.
What do you think?
Excuse me.
No.
Get out of my face.
Kiss my ass!
Shut up, breanna.
Welcome back to Milwaukee.
My name is Nathaniel Jones.
I'm from mount zion, Wisconsin.
I'm 22 years old, and I'm
a civil war re-enactor.
Aah!
So basically, civil war
reenacting is, you dress up, go
out onto a field somewhere, and
you just recreate a battle that
actually took place.
Aah!
Put the gun down.
He actually is gonna
point the gun at me.
I actually think
he's gonna shoot me.
We can just talk about it.
Don't try me.
Let's just talk.
Don't try me, man!
But this soldier isn't
going into battle alone.
Today he's brought along his father, a
man he's just a little passionate about.
People would come up to me and
ask me, "is your dad a hippie?
Your dad looks like a hippie.
He looks like a hippie.
Does he smoke pot?
Does your dad smoke pot?"
No, he's not a hippie.
Hippies believe in sex.
♪
He's not a hippie.
He hasn't gone anywhere with anybody
since my mom left, so... ♪
♪
Uh-oh.
Oh, no.
Hello, sir.
Hello, corporal.
Good afternoon, sir.
What is your name?
My name is Nathaniel Jones.
What is with the outfit,
the civil war outfit?
I mean... I do civil war reenacting
as a hobby, and I got the uniform
at various reenactments, piece by piece,
until I had it all put together.
Awesome.
What song are you gonna sing now?
The lion sleeps tonight.
Okay.
♪ Wee Dee Dee Dee ♪
♪ Dee Dee Dee Dee Dee ♪
♪ Dee wee um um away ♪
♪ wee Dee Dee Dee ♪
♪ Dee Dee Dee Dee Dee ♪
♪ wee um um away ♪
Ut, ut.
♪ In the village ♪
♪ the peaceful village ♪
♪ the lion sleeps tonight ♪
♪ near the village ♪
♪ the quiet village ♪
♪ the lion sleeps tonight ♪
♪ eee-eee-eee ♪
♪ wee um um away ♪
Wow, that was... what was
the word you used before?
What was it?
You said, uh, outstanding.
Thank you.
You're very welcome.
What are
we doing in here?
Well, no, you know, I'm not sure if
it's, you know, for American idol.
I'm not sure about that, but
I certainly liked the song.
I liked it a lot.
Okay.
Yeah.
It's... I'm sorry.
It's a no for me.
Anything I can do to
change your mind?
Any other songs?
We kind of got the measure of what
you are, you know what I mean?
All right.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Wow.
Commitment.
Yeah.
So Nathaniel becomes another
casualty of the day, and the
awkward evening turns to night.
But that's not the only showdown the
judges were gonna have in Milwaukee.
Oh, man, you guys
make me so nervous.
You want to turn that way
and just take a breath?
All right.
Compose yourself.
Deep breath.
And then you can turn
around when you're ready.
That's very cool.
All right.
♪ As I sit here ♪
♪ and slowly close my eyes ♪
♪ and feel the wind ♪
♪ pass through my body ♪
♪ I'm the one in your soul ♪
♪ freedom with your energize ♪
♪ I need serenity ♪
♪ nothing changes ♪
♪ days go by ♪
Okay, should we vote?
Nah, we didn't make it.
Oh, that's all right.
Yeah, that's... that was...
that... that was really rough.
I don't know.
As the sting of rejection sets
in for Mason, it's a good
thing the next contestant already
has success on her side.
My name is Molly dewolf swenson.
I am 22 years old, from
Seattle, Washington.
I recently graduated
from Harvard university.
♪
I applied sort of randomly for
an internship at the white house
and ended up getting it.
♪
I'm now working in the
white house for the Obama
administration as an intern, and I
am in love with this president.
Not in the Monica lewinsky/bill
Clinton intern/president sort of way.
Just in a platonic way.
How are you?
I'm doing great.
Very, very good.
Randy, I've got to call
you out for one second.
This morning, you were really
excited, so I don't think you
noticed, but as you were running
down the line, high-fiving
everyone, we totally missed hands and
you kind of punched me in the mouth.
Oh, I didn't mean to.
Are you saying that I've
injured your singing voice?
There's a little... no, no, no.
The singing voice should be
fine, but... did you bleed?
Did it, like, it cut you?
I hope you don't add
insult to real injury.
I mean... oh, come on.
Didn't you feel yourself
punch somebody in the mouth?
I didn't at all.
I didn't even know.
No, I know you didn't, and that's
why I'm not holding it against you.
Somebody else did it.
I hit the hand and they accidentally...
nope, nope, it was your big
old hand just in my face.
You've got to forgive him, for
he knows not what he does.
Forgive me.
I know not what thou
art this doest.
Hey... on behalf of the... ma'am,
we're sorry about your lip.
But welcome, though.
Thanks.
Finally.
Good to be here.
You still in school or
did you just graduate?
I just graduated from Harvard.
You went to Harvard?
Mmm.
What are you gonna do?
I mean, I don't know
exactly what I want to do.
I'm an intern at the
white house right now.
What?
Harvard, white house.
You're an intern at
the white house?
Yeah.
Okay.
Uh, from the white house
to American idol.
I like it.
What are you gonna sing?
I'm gonna sing, sitting
on the dock of the bay.
Okay.
♪ I'm gonna sit ♪
♪ on the dock of the bay ♪
♪ watchin' the tide ♪
♪ roll away ♪
♪ I left my home in Georgia ♪
♪ headed for the frisco bay ♪
♪ 'cause I got ♪
♪ nothing to live for ♪
♪ nothing's gonna come my way ♪
♪ I'm gonna sit ♪
♪ on the dock of the bay ♪
♪ wasting time ♪
Mmm!
Mmm! Wow. Who knew?
Who knew what's going
on at the white house?
Impressive.
That's... yeah.
That... that's great.
That's great.
You've got attitude.
You know where to put it.
Oh, jeez.
That was beautiful.
Yeah.
Thank you, sir.
So, real pitch.
The way you started down there
like that, well, I knew, I knew
you were gonna go
somewhere with that.
I think you're terrific.
I think that's great.
Thank you.
Just... I liked it too.
I was impressed at how low you
started too, and it sounded
really rich down there, which
is a tough thing, and tough to
control when you're nervous, which I
can tell a little bit that you are.
No, really?
I'm just a little puzzled,
because, I mean, you're a really
good singer, so where
have you been?
What's been going on?
She's been at Harvard.
I've been at Harvard.
She's only 22.
She just graduated.
That's what I've been doing.
Voting, voting.
Let's vote.
Randy?
Yes.
Jennifer.
Steven.
Yes, and you're
going to Hollywood!
Yeah, baby!
Thank you so much, you guys.
That's how you do it
from the white house.
Wow.
From the white house to Hollywood.
Gotta represent the
administration.
Come on, right?
Tell Obama we need you.
Congratulations.
Thank you so much, you guys.
Good job!
Oh, thanks for being
my stand-in family.
Yes, I'm here.
Man, this first day here in
Milwaukee is crazy, man.
There's some good finds here.
What is going on?
I figure we should just call
the white house and tell them.
Yeah, yeah.
I can get them on a press call.
Call Barack and
tell him you're in.
That was... wow, wow, wow.
That was an amazing day.
Yeah.
Amazing day, Milwaukee, man.
I can't even believe it.
So Randy gives Molly his stamp of approval
and a golden ticket to Hollywood.
♪ My heart tonight ♪
After the break, it's
day two in Milwaukee.
♪ This time ♪
♪ it's gonna be different ♪
But the judges have their hands
full with more amazing talent.
You're going to Hollywood!
And as the competition intensifies...
Oh, my God!
Wow.
Randy's not playing Mr. nice guy.
Uh, I thought it was
terrible and a joke.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
And later, one of our best
singers has an amazing story.
What kind of guy would I be if I walked
out when she needed me the most?
Stay tuned.
♪
♪ hey ♪
Welcome back to Wisconsin, y'all.
It's day two of our
Milwaukee audition.
Milwaukee rocks!
And everyone's still basking in
the glow of yesterday's talent.
What a lovely day.
Look at this.
Wow, hot.
It's gonna be hot again today.
Day two, Milwaukee.
Here we go.
♪ When I'm out walking ♪
♪ I strut my stuff ♪
This is a rock star crossing.
♪ Let me go on ♪
♪ like a blister in the sun ♪
♪ let me go on ♪
There's good feelings all around as the
Bradley center is filled with even more
enthusiasm.
Why are we gonna find the
next idol here in Milwaukee?
What's the talent like?
Okay, we have summerfest,
we have Danny gokey.
We're on radar on the United States, and
I believe I'm the next American idol.
This could be the next American
idol now, so prepare yourself.
♪ Nants ingonyama ♪
♪ bagithi baba ♪
♪ sithi uhm ingonyama ♪
♪ let me go on ♪
♪ like a blister in the sun ♪
♪ good morning ♪
♪ good ♪
Second day in Milwaukee.
Let's go, baby.
Let's get it done.
I hope it's as good as yesterday.
As our judges take their seats and
get warmed up for the day... ♪ aah ♪
Okay.
♪ Ah ♪
♪ ahhhh ♪
The first contestant of day two has
had over a year to do just that.
Hi.
Hello.
How's it going?
Good.
How's it going with you?
Yeah.
Great.
Oh, what a beautiful
sight I've got here.
Oh, nice, huh?
I was gonna say the
same thing about you.
Thank you.
Curly hair.
I love the shoes.
Thanks.
What's your name?
Hayley.
Hayley, what's it all about?
This is everything I want.
Yeah?
You done this before?
I might have.
Yes, once.
Yeah, and?
Where?
Last season, Chicago.
And what went wrong?
Um... or right?
I don't know.
You guys told me to come
back and, um, I was crushed.
Well, I wasn't there, see?
So it's gonna be different today.
Randy was there.
But I-I-I came back.
She's holding a grudge.
Wait a minute.
Hang on.
Do you think that you've improved?
Oh, definitely.
What are you gonna sing?
Let's do some oh, darlin' for you.
Oh, yeah.
Rock it out, right?
Yeah.
All right.
♪ Oh, darlin' ♪
♪ well, if you leave me ♪
♪ well, I'll never make it ♪
♪ alone ♪
♪ no ♪
♪ believe me when I beg you ♪
♪ don't ever leave me alone ♪
There we go.
Yeah, yeah.
All right, all right.
♪ 'Cause this time ♪
♪ it gon' be different ♪
♪ yeah ♪
Oh, damn, what a beautiful
choice of notes.
When you hit one note in the
middle there, I went, that's it.
Hello, ba-ding!
You know, you hit that, and
it... yeah, that was so nice.
Ba-ding!
I like that, ba-ding!
That was so, so good.
Okay, with the ba-ding.
I liked it.
Yeah, I liked you too.
I think you've gotten so
much better, actually.
Thanks, Randy.
You always had the potential, I
think, even when we saw you before.
It's just the control, 'cause
if you gonna sing all those
runs, you gotta really be able
to sing 'em and close 'em and
loop 'em and the whole thing.
Mmm!
Let's take a vote.
Yes!
Randy, yes.
Welcome to Hollywood.
Thank you.
Oh, mwah!
You're beautiful.
Welcome to hollyweird, baby.
Congratulations, baby.
That was good.
Yes!
Oh, my God.
You did it!
We're going to Hollywood!
So this Chicago native has earned
a one-way ticket to tinseltown.
And fellow windy city resident
Taiwan hopes he can join her there.
When I walk into that room,
I'm gonna give them me.
I'm gonna leave no room for doubt.
Time to get out there and
show the world Taiwan strong.
♪ Let me tell you ♪
♪ 'bout a place ♪
♪ somewhere up in New York way ♪
♪ where the people are so gay ♪
♪ twistin' the night away ♪
♪ here they have a lot of fun ♪
♪ putting trouble on the run ♪
♪ man, you find the old ♪
♪ and young ♪
♪ twistin' the night away ♪
♪ they're twistin' ♪
♪ twistin', man ♪
♪ everybody's feeling great ♪
♪ they're twistin' ♪
♪ twistin' ♪
♪ the night away ♪
Who are you with?
Taiwan strong.
Taiwan. I met Taiwan.
I like him. He's fun.
Yes.
Steven.
Okay.
I see the sparkle in your eyes,
you know, and I liked your voice.
I like you, man.
Randy.
I thought you sounded great.
Very controlled, nice tone.
You did a good job with it.
I think you did a really
good job with it.
Thank you. Thank you.
You got me thinking... I say yes.
Thank you.
I say yes.
Welcome to Hollywood, baby.
Thank you.
♪
To God be the glory.
I told you.
You got a Charley horse?
Oh, my God.
We got a Charley horse here.
I got a Charley horse.
I'm going to American idol!
Oh, my God!
We got a Charley horse here.
Ooh.
To God be the glory.
Are you having a... what's
wrong with you, girl?
Are you cramping?
Man, I'm excited.
I'm excited.
Oh, my God.
Hollywood, here we come.
Does that tickle?
All right, you're
stealing the show.
Okay, now, now just straighten up.
There you go.
Okay.
Well, you know, drink
lots of water.
♪
We're gonna help her out
and come back after this.
Anybody know shiatsu?
Coming up, more amazing
talent delivers in Milwaukee.
Plus, is this the most
annoying girl in the world?
Whoo!
Welcome back to American
idol here in Milwaukee.
As you can see, still
thousands left to audition.
And every single person in the crowd
today was ready for their close-up.
Say cheese!
Cheese!
Especially this cheese head.
His coworkers are gonna be
shocked to find him here.
My name is Steve bagoon, and I'm
a certified public accountant.
I've been a cpa for
about 3 1/2 years.
I work for one of the big
four accounting firms.
♪ Working in a coal mine ♪
♪ going down, down, down ♪
I'm an auditor.
So I really don't have
that many friends.
It sort of comes with
the territory I guess.
It's a lot like seeing the state
patrol on the interstate.
People can't wait
for you to go away.
During the day, you're crunching
numbers, and then you
get to actually have a little fun.
At night, you go out
and sing here locally?
Not really.
I'm pretty much a wedding
and funeral singer.
Weddings tend to be more fun.
Getting a golden ticket to
Hollywood would be incredible.
I feel like I'm ready.
I'm ready to step it up.
How long can this go on?
Push it.
That's awkward.
♪ Working in a coal mine ♪
Come on in.
What's your name?
My name's Steve bagoon.
Is that right?
Yeah.
The name's kind of funny because
you probably heard it, and you
assumed what my body type
was gonna look like.
Yeah.
Gigantic.
Big goon.
Bagoon. Big goon.
That's it.
All right.
You do standup as well?
Yeah.
I'm an accountant.
Whoa, God, there's two strikes.
I hope you can sing
better than that joke.
♪ Going back to the corner ♪
♪ where I first saw you ♪
♪ going to camp ♪
♪ in my sleeping bag ♪
♪ I'm not gonna move ♪
♪ I know it makes no sense ♪
♪ what else can I do? ♪
♪ how can I move on ♪
♪ when I'm still in love ♪
♪ with you? ♪
♪ thinking maybe you'd come ♪
♪ back here to a place ♪
♪ that we'd meet ♪
♪ and you'll see me waiting ♪
♪ for you ♪
♪ on the corner of the street ♪
♪ 'cause I'm not moving ♪
♪ I'm not moving ♪
Okay.
I don't think I've heard
anybody sing here yet that hit
that note that resonates
in this room.
I heard that echo,
just kept going.
Thank you.
So surprising.
An accountant. Who knew?
'Cause you're big, and
your voice is high.
It was like, what the... my little son,
two years old, he goes, "what the...
What the..."
I found you to be
disturbingly great.
Weird, compelling, great.
A certain something that, you know...
Different.
Yeah. Really different.
Thank you.
I say yes.
I say yes too.
Ooh-ooh.
Three yeses.
Yes! Yes!
Jennifer, where is that man going?
You're going to Hollywood.
Yeah!
I'll practice.
♪ I'm not moving ♪
This is what I've
been waiting for.
Everything else is
icing on the cake.
I'm pumped.
♪
Going back to the corner ♪
I'm an accountant.
This is fun.
Yes!
Day two is off to a strong
start as our first-ever
accountant cashes in on
a trip to Hollywood.
We'll see you there.
Whoo!
Let's hope Milwaukee
can go two for two.
Hello, hello, hello.
What is your name?
My name is vernika Patterson.
Vernika.
What's up?
What are you gonna sing?
Um, minnie riperton's loving you.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
Just start?
♪ Loving you ♪
♪ is easy 'cause ♪
♪ you're beautiful ♪
♪ mm... ♪
Sorry, can I start it over?
Yeah.
I'm nervous.
The lady looking at me.
I won't look. I won't look.
I just want to run up there and,
like, hug her, but I can't.
Lady, don't look at her, lady.
I'm sorry.
Okay. That's me.
How about if we all
just kind of look away?
No, because then it's
not... here we go.
What should we do?
Tell us.
You the judge.
Okay, I'm gonna start over.
♪ Loving you ♪
♪ is more than just the dream ♪
♪ come true ♪
♪ and everything that I do ♪
♪ is out of loving you ♪
♪ la la la la la ♪
♪ la la la la la la la la la ♪
♪ la ♪
♪ Oohhh ♪
♪ no one else can ♪
♪ make me feel ♪
Vernika.
Okay.
You know, that's such
a beautiful song.
Thank you.
Uh, vernika, this is not
gonna work for this.
And why is that?
Like, seriously, I can sing another
song, like, with no problem.
I'm not sure if you're ready
for American idol right now.
Really? You think so?
Yeah. Well...
That's what it appears to me.
Half of these people cannot
sing better than me.
Like, seriously.
No.
I'm not even upset.
Huh?
Good.
Yeah.
We're just trying to
be honest with you.
'Cause hopefully that will help you
if you're trying to be a singer.
No, seriously, is it because I'm not
skinny like half of these females in here?
Oh, no.
No, I think it is.
No, that has nothing
to do with it.
Baby, tell me about this guy here.
That's a man.
I'm talking about female.
This girl's not skinny.
I'm bigger than her.
That first winner wasn't... this
is not about size or look.
You know what, thank you.
It's about talent.
Mm.
I guess that's a no.
I guess she gave herself a no.
She said no to Hollywood.
She said no.
We didn't even have to say no.
So what do you think?
Excuse me.
What do you think
about the others?
♪ Sunshine, lollipops ♪
♪ and rainbows ♪
♪ everything that's wonderful ♪
I don't want to be on camera.
♪ We're together ♪
♪ brighter than a lucky penny ♪
♪
She took that really
well, though, I thought.
I can sing better than half of these
people in this competition and as well as
some of these singers.
Excuse me.
But vernika wasn't the only one
on day two not having happy days.
Damn American idol
can kiss my ass.
It sucks.
I'm sorry.
I really wanted this really bad.
♪ When you're in love ♪
♪ to stay ♪
I don't want to talk.
Get out of my face, okay?
They've been letting people
in that cannot sing!
I want to [bleep] punch those
people in the [bleep]...
get that camera out my face.
You want me to kick you in
your [bleep], you better get
the [bleep] out of my way.
Shut up, breanna.
Could you seriously get the
[bleep] camera away from me?
Coming up... I want you to stay
tuned to your televisions.
Not the best Barack,
but can he rock?
I like that. Ooh.
Plus, we will get this
line from Jennifer.
You might be my favorite I've seen so far
we are back to Wisconsin.
Over the past two days, we've
seen some talented performers
here in Milwaukee, including our
first-ever white house intern.
Little does she know she's about
to get trumped by the man himself.
Thank you.
I have come to Milwaukee because
I want the American people to
see the type of talent that this
man, Albert Rogers III, possesses.
God bless American idol, and
God bless Albert Rogers III,
and bless the united
states of America.
Thank you.
Yo, yo, what's up, man?
What's going on?
Hi.
Come on in.
So what is your name, sir?
My name is Albert Rogers III.
And how old are you, Albert?
I am 24.
Really?
Yeah.
Do I look younger, Randy?
I wouldn't quite say that.
Oh, I look older.
No, he didn't say that.
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
Who do people say you
sound like when you sing?
I've gotten ruben studdard.
Of course.
So if you've got ruben, you must have
gotten Luther probably, 'cause it's all...
I've gotten Luther, yes.
So, um, and a little Usher, but...
Wow.
Maybe not so much.
Luther and Usher,
that's a wide gap.
I'm putting it out...
That's a lot of great singers right there.
Well, you got to Usher yoself
rht into an American idol.
Come on now.
What you gonna sing, baby?
Stand by me.
Good.
♪ When the night ♪
♪ has come ♪
♪ oh ♪
♪ and the land is dark ♪
♪ and the moon ♪
♪ is the only light ♪
♪ we'll see ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ no, I won't ♪
♪ be afraid ♪
Wow. All right.
All right, all right, so...
I never heard anybody squeeze
the flavor of that song.
You squeezed it out so slow,
it was like, you know, vanilla
Fudge and Eleanor rigby.
I liked it.
Huh?
I'm not sure... I'm not sure
if it's American idol stuff.
You think?
But I liked it.
Uh, I thought it was
terrible and a joke.
Hey.
It's just not serious.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I didn't... let's wrap... what...
do we even need to vote?
Yes, we do.
I say no.
I say no this time too.
You're not up for this.
But thanks for coming out, Albert.
Thank you.
Good looking out, baby.
Thank you, guys.
Okay.
Wow.
Poor baby.
Even though Albert did not make it today,
he will be something big someday.
So I want you to stay tuned, America,
because things are about to shake up.
What a surprise that was.
Next.
But something tells me the
judges will be even more
surprised by student
teacher Scott dangerfield.
You know, I'm colorblind,
but, unless you borrowed my
lipstick, is that your real lips?
This is my real lip.
If it is, then... I was kissing one
of the girls backstage before.
I knew it.
Nice.
Did it rub off?
I'm sorry.
You found love in the idol line?
I did, man.
Love in the idol line.
A lot of girls out there.
More than one destiny's
gonna be made for me today.
Wow, man, come on.
Come on.
Wow.
♪ Come on ♪
♪ come on ♪
♪ now take it ♪
♪ take another little bit ♪
♪ of my lipstick, baby ♪
What are you gonna sing?
How about amos Lee?
You know amos Lee?
Dreamin' by amos Lee?
Yeah.
Yeah? All right.
♪ My soul is as open ♪
♪ as the sky ♪
♪ oftentimes it as just ♪
♪ as blue ♪
Mm.
Mm-hmm.
♪ Sometimes it's for ♪
♪ the glory ♪
Mm.
♪ Oh, but mostly ♪
♪ it's the love ♪
Ah.
Mm.
♪ It's the love ♪
You might be my favorite
I've seen so far.
I'm your favorite?
Oh, my God, Jennifer Lopez.
You blew me away.
I swear.
Dude.
Wow. Wow.
Crazy. Crazy.
Let's vote!
Let's vote.
I want to vote.
Yeah, go ahead.
Wow.
Yes!
Uh, yes.
Randy?
100 million percent yes.
You know what I'm loving?
Hollywood.
This is the unassuming season.
Never judge a book by its cover.
Dude, you were hot.
Keep the hair.
Keep the glasses.
I like all of it.
You my favorite. Okay.
We'll see you in Hollywood.
Hollywood!
Hollywood.
We've been waiting
all day for you.
Wow.
The way he moved his body, he
felt the music in his body.
Wow.
Jennifer Lopez said I was
her favorite so far.
About your singing?
I almost fainted at that
point, but I caught myself.
You know, I blacked out a little.
Did you give... did you
give her my number?
Coming up...
Someone gets Steven's attention.
Why, you look like you could
be one of my [bleep].
Nope.
You guys might want to get a room.
Plus, he's triumphed
over incredible tragedy.
But can he win the judges'
approval?
Stay tuned to find out.
Welcome back to our
Milwaukee auditions.
The people of Wisconsin
are a proud bunch.
Hey.
This state is home to some of
the most loyal and dedicated
sports fans in the entire country.
Well, green bay is the
home of the packers.
The packers.
We love the packers.
The Milwaukee braves.
Oh, wait a minute.
They moved, didn't they?
Somewhere down this line might be the
most colorful fan we've seen yet.
Whoo!
My passion is the
green bay packers.
Go, pack, go!
Whoo!
Welcome to l-l-l-lambeau!
I became a huge packer
fan because of my dad.
It's unforgiven-able.
It's one of those sins you
cannot do is not be a green bay
packer fan in our home.
Game day Sundays at my household...
Whoo!
Oh, it's... it's an
intense environment.
Go, pack, go!
- I've been known to get up, be disgusted...
- Go, pack, go!
Yelling, throw things.
Love the green and gold.
Hey, guys.
Hi.
Hey.
How are you all?
Good. How are you?
Hi. What's your name?
I'm Megan frasier, and I've
actually never been better.
Yeah, you've never been better.
Where are you from?
I'm from green bay, Wisconsin.
Yeah?
Go, pack, go.
Go, pack... packo?
What do you say?
Go, pack, go, like, go, packers.
Oh, go, pack, go.
Like...
Go, pack, go!
Oh, she's a real
performer right here.
We got a live one right here.
Yeah.
Well.
We got to love it.
Got to love the pack.
What are you gonna sing?
Baby by Justin bieber.
Of course. Of course.
Wow.
♪ And I was like, baby ♪
♪ baby, baby ♪
♪ ohh ♪
♪ like baby, baby ♪
♪ baby, ohh ♪
♪ like baby, baby, baby ♪
♪ ohh ♪
♪ You'd always be mine ♪
♪ mine ♪
The glass broke.
That was beautiful.
Okay, look, I had enough.
The only thing missing
is the cheese head.
It's not ♪ ba-ad ♪
I'm not ♪ bad ♪
Wow.
Yeah, okay.
You want this to
take this by storm.
Like, I mean you've had... storm.
But you've had your country
singers and your beat-boxers.
It's time for some opera.
Like, look at this.
Self-imposed opera of
a Justin bieber song.
You're right.
That's what I've been
looking for all my life.
I know. Who hasn't?
Who hasn't?
Should we just vote?
Yeah.
Yes.
Well, that was fun.
Should we do it... should
we vote together?
I know it's gonna be a
rounding... one, two, three.
Yes!
No.
It's all right. Thanks.
Well, you gave it the
old... it was fun.
You should do stand-up.
The old college team try.
Yes, thank you, sweetie.
Thanks. Have a good one.
Nice meeting you all.
Nice meeting you too.
Good luck to the packers.
Thanks. Super bowl winners.
I don't know about that.
No?
It's a no.
Ahh.
So it looks like Megan's not
gonna be your idol this year.
But Allie jados has been waiting
her whole life to meet hers.
Are you excited today?
I am really excited.
Tell me about that excitement.
Steven Tyler's, like,
one of my idols.
Like, when I saw him
walk out, I cried.
You cried.
I was, like, pouring tears.
It's surreal, seriously.
I auditioned because I want to
bring an edge, I want to bring
more rock and roll
to American idol.
Good luck, Allie.
Nice to chat with you.
It was nice to meet you too.
We're gonna send you in.
Oh. Okay.
I would freak out if Steven Tyler
told me I was going to Hollywood.
I would freak out.
Hello.
Hi.
Wow.
What's your name?
Allie.
Allie?
Yeah.
Why, you look like you
could be one of my...Nope.
Friends. One of your friends.
One of my friends.
That's it.
Hi. What's it all about?
Oh, my God, this is crazy.
I'm sorry.
I know. It's funny.
Jennifer, there's a thing with
these two, like, she can't speak.
Steven's lost for words.
Very rare.
Tell me a little bit
about yourself.
Um, I love you.
Obviously, we can kind
of tell something.
I'm thinking maybe a
hug is in line here.
Oh, my God.
Yes, please.
Oh, my God, this is too cool.
This is too cool.
It gets better.
It gets better. Watch.
Okay.
I don't know about you,
Jennifer, but when you guys
hugged, I could hear some
bells in the background.
Birds chirping.
Birds and bells.
Oh, my God.
What are you into?
Who do you like to sing?
Um, I love the Beatles.
I love rock and roll.
Aerosmith.
Aerosmith. I love aerosmith.
Seen you guys
probably seven times.
Nice.
So far.
What are you gonna sing tonight?
I'm gonna sing come
together by the Beatles.
Nice. Nice choice.
♪ Here come, old flat top ♪
♪ he come groovin' up slowly ♪
♪ he got do-do eyeball ♪
♪ he one holy roller ♪
♪ he got hair down ♪
♪ to his knees ♪
♪ got to be a joker ♪
♪ he just do what he please ♪
♪ come together ♪
♪ right now ♪
♪ over me ♪
Wow.
In the immortal words of John Lennon...
Do you know anymore?
Yes.
Do you know any aerosmith songs?
Yeah.
Which one?
Why don't you sing a
little bit of something?
I could do dream on.
I can't do the end, like the...
Oh, you got to have the end.
I can't.
You sing it, let Steven
do the end part.
Here we go.
Start it.
♪ Yeah, dream on ♪
♪ dream on ♪
♪ dream until your drm ♪
♪ come true ♪
♪ Yeah, dream on ♪
♪ dream on, dream on ♪
♪ dream on ♪
Okay.
I can't get there.
It's hard for her to sing her
idol's song in front of her idol.
I know it's tough.
Oh, you will have your
turn in the barrel.
Whoa, yes, I love that.
That's not easy to do.
That was fun, though.
That was really fun, yeah.
I'm sorry I screwed it up.
It's hard for me because I so appreciate
you sang, you know, my song there.
Um, very pitchy.
You know, you know, you jump all
over the place with your notes.
That kind of scares me.
I know I can do it.
I want this so bad.
Oh.
I think you have a great
quality in your voice.
And I think you have some really
good performance quality,
which comes alive onstage.
Mm-hmm.
I'm not sure if you're ready yet.
I'm gonna say no.
I don't know. I don't know.
Well, I disagree.
I'm gonna say yes.
We haven't seen anyone like her.
She has great performance quality.
Jennifer, this is crazy, though.
You know what's
happening right now?
I said no, you said yes.
Steven Tyler, your idol,
is on the hot seat.
Your fate lies in his hands.
♪ It went by ♪
♪ like dusk to dawn ♪
I don't know, Randy.
I kind of, you know, like, agreed with you...
About the cars we take here.
Right.
But as far as her goes...
I say yes.
You're going to Hollywood!
♪ Nobody knows ♪
Thank you. Thank you.
Steven Tyler put you through.
This is crazy.
♪ You got to lose ♪
That was great. That was good.
♪ Sing, women ♪
♪ sing for the year ♪
♪ sing for the laughter ♪
♪ sing for the tears ♪
♪ sing, women ♪
That was great.
She was good.
That was pretty sweet.
Good.
Steven, I love you.
Thank you so much for
putting me through.
You won't regret it, I promise.
Aw.
♪ Dream on, dream on ♪
♪ dream until your dream ♪
♪ come true ♪
But Allie was one of 56 in
Milwaukee whose dream continued.
Oh, boy.
♪ Dream on ♪
♪ Dream on, dream on ♪
♪ dream on ♪
♪ dream on, ohhh ♪
♪
After this, the Milwaukee
auditions come to a close.
But there's one more contestant
who has an amazing instrument.
Oh. Oh.
Nice.
And an amazing story
to go with it.
Are you married, dude?
I'm engaged.
It's just about closing
time here in Milwaukee.
The thousands have filtered
through the stadium and made
their way into the judging room.
Along the way, we've discovered
some sensational talent.
♪ I've been really trying ♪
♪ baby ♪
♪ trying to hold back ♪
♪ this feeling for so long ♪
♪ should I give up ♪
♪ or should I just keep ♪
♪ chasing pavements ♪
♪ even if it leads nowhere ♪
♪ and I can't believe ♪
♪ how much it turns me on ♪
♪ just to be your man ♪
But before we pack up and say
our good-byes to Wisconsin...
That's what I'm talking about.
Hollywood.
We'd like you to meet Chicago
native Chris medina.
Yo, what's up, man?
How's it going?
Hey.
Come on in.
How are you?
What's your name?
My name is Chris medina.
Nice to meet you.
How old are you?
I am 26 years old.
26?
And you're from?
What's the matter?
I just can't believe I'm
standing in front of you guys.
That's awesome.
What a trip, huh?
Are you married, dude?
No, I'm engaged.
I'm engaged.
Your girlfriend know you're here?
She is that her ring?
This is her ring.
See it?
What a lover.
Tell us about her.
Uh, well... julianne and I have
been together for eight years.
We've been engaged for
two going on three.
♪ She says wake up ♪
♪ it's no use pretending ♪
You know, after we got engaged,
we kind of made it a
promise to get married two
years after the engagement.
But on October 2, 2009, she...
she got into an accident.
Everything changed.
We're still not married.
♪ One of us will die ♪
♪ inside these arms ♪
She suffered a traumatic
brain injury.
Even though the doctors were
saying that she wasn't gonna
make it, I believed
that she was going to.
I just felt there's no way
she's not gonna wake up.
I didn't know what to
expect after that.
But I certainly knew that
she wasn't gonna die.
And a month and a half
later, she woke up.
♪ Ashes round the yard ♪
Her mother and I are
her caretakers.
Aw, you're doing great, hon.
I was about to make vows just
two months from the accident.
You know?
Through thick and thin, till
death do us part, in sickness
and in health, for
better or for worse.
What kind of guy would I be if I walked
out when she needed me the most?
♪ I lay smiling ♪
If I were to make it to
Hollywood, I feel like it would
get her to be happy
about something again.
I think I would have already won.
I felt like I would have
already won something.
Do you want to know
what I'm gonna sing?
Yeah.
How does that work?
I'm gonna sing breakeven
by the script.
Go for it.
♪ Oh, I'm still alive ♪
♪ but I'm barely breathing ♪
♪ just pray to a God ♪
♪ that I don't believe in ♪
♪ ohh ♪
♪ and I got time ♪
♪ while she got her freedom ♪
♪ 'cause when a heart breaks ♪
♪ no, it don't break even ♪
♪ even ♪
♪ ohh ♪
♪ what am I gonna do ♪
♪ when the best part of me ♪
♪ was always you ♪
♪ and what am I supposed ♪
♪ to say ♪
♪ when I'm all choked up ♪
♪ that you're okay ♪
♪ yeah ♪
♪ I'm falling to pieces ♪
♪ when a heart breaks ♪
♪ no, it don't break even ♪
Oh. Oh.
Nice. Nice.
Go get your girlfriend.
You got to bring her
back, introduce us.
We got to meet her.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, please.
Oh, my God, that
would make her day.
Yeah.
Go get that girl, man.
Okay, I will.
They want to meet Julie.
Okay. Come on, guys.
I got to tell you, man, I
am so happy right now.
♪ Ten miles from town ♪
♪ and I just broke down ♪
♪ spitting out smoke ♪
Hi.
Hello.
How are you?
Hey, you.
Hello.
I'm Randy. Hi.
How are you?
This is Jennifer.
Hi, I'm Jennifer Lopez.
Nice to meet you.
Steven Tyler.
I just heard your fiance sing.
And he's so good.
You know, 'cause he sings
to you all the time.
I could tell.
I love that.
That's why he sings so good,
'cause he sings to you.
So, listen, Chris, you got three yeses
from Steven, Jennifer, and myself.
We discussed it while
you were outside.
We discussed it when you
went out to get her.
Dude, you're going to Hollywood.
Chris medina, Hollywood-bound.
♪ As long as I'm laughing ♪
♪ with you ♪
♪ and I think that ♪
♪ all that still matters ♪
Really sweet.
Nice kid.
He sang great.
Wow.
Good singer.
She said, "I knew it."
I'm going to Hollywood.
Ow!
Next time, we'll be coming
to you from Nashville, where
idol takes over the streets,
and music city plays along in
one of our largest turnouts ever.
These big numbers
mean big surprises.
Wow!
Nashville's bringing out the
animal in Steven Tyler!
And somewhere in this crowd,
a star is discovered.
Best I've seen today.
Yes!
I think we found the one today.
While Nashville is just the
beginning for some... yes!
You are going to Hollywood!
Many will be singing the blues.
Get the [bleep] out of my face!
She's full of [bleep].
And it's sure to be one
that can't be missed.
♪ Eeeh eeeh eeeh ♪
♪ ah ha ha ♪
Sync by Behzadt
www.addic7ed.com