So you can sing
high notes, right?
Very high.
What's... hit me a
high one right now.
Okay, um...
All right, Nashville, come on.
♪ Ah ♪
♪ ah-ah-ah-oh ♪
Wow.
For the just the second time in
our ten seasons, idol's tour
of America has brought us deep into
the land of hopes and dreams...
Nashville, Tennessee.
We've had a report of 10,000 people
waiting in front of bridgestone arena.
But in fact, we were
taking over the streets...
As the crowd soon swelled
to a staggering 17,000.
Yeah!
He can do it!
The judges are ready to find the talent...
Hey. Good morning.
And across the street, the
contestants are ready to deliver
the goods, each one of them
hoping to garner the success
of country's biggest star...
Carrie Underwood, who recently
added "grand ole opry" member to
her already-impressive resume.
So we thought it was appropriate
to hold our auditions in the
opry's most famous home...
the ryman auditorium.
It's a legendary venue with
17,000 legends in the making.
Bring 'em all in, line
'em up, let's go.
♪ Ooh-ee ♪
Who will continue
Carrie's legacy?
Probably not this girl.
I'm Christine McCaffrey, and
I'm 27 years old, and I'm
originally from Springfield,
Missouri, and now I live in
west palm beach, Florida.
And what do you do in
west palm beach, Florida?
I'm a dental assistant.
Great. Is that fun?
It's lot of fun.
I really love making
people have a happy smile.
I'm gonna twinkle like a star,
and I'm gonna make the universe
a better place, because I
have the gift that will make
everybody else respond
to what I have.
Thank you.
Okay. Bye.
Bye.
Do I go to the second door too?
No, go this way.
♪ Suh uh oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ oh oh oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ suh uh oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ obsessed, ah-ah-ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ ah ah ah ah ah ah ♪
Oh, my God!
What is this?
We're on American idol.
No!
Mm-hmm.
Do you do voiceovers
for cartoons?
I don't know!
You should.
You should do.
Really?
Really!
Really, really.
Okay.
So what are you gonna sing?
I have Lee womack, uh,
I hope you can dance.
Oh, one of my favorite songs.
Great song.
Okay. Go.
Okay.
♪ I hope you never ♪
♪ lose your sense of wonder ♪
Oh, come on!
♪ I hope you ♪
♪ get your fill to eat ♪
♪ but always keep that hunger ♪
♪ May you never take ♪
♪ one single breath ♪
♪ for granted ♪
Really.
♪ God forbid ♪
♪ he ever leave you ♪
♪ empty-handed ♪
♪ I hope ♪
♪ you dance ♪
♪ I hope you dance ♪
Really?
♪ Hope you never take ♪
♪ one single breath ♪
♪ for granted ♪
Really?
Really.
Okay, sweetie.
We're gonna vote, okay?
Yeah, we're gonna vote.
Sounds good.
I'm gonna say no.
Awesome.
It's a no.
You're not serious, are you?
I'm very serious about going
on in American idol, 'cause I
have the ability to write lyrics, and
I have the ability to sing them.
Do you have the ability
to read minds?
What am I thinking right now?
Hmm... I think it's a yes!
No. You can't read minds.
That's for sure!
What would you like me to sing?
I'll sing anything.
I just want you to go that way.
I'll do that too.
Have a nice day.
Thank you so much for your time.
That's not serious.
No, she was serious.
No!
And you were mean!
I'm not buyin' it.
I can't buy it.
Just say no and let it be.
I thought I was nice.
Your mother would like
to hear the good news.
Oh. I did my best, and
I got... I am so glad.
I got one yes and two nos.
That's okay.
I'm proud of you.
You did?
I did.
Who said yes?
Uh, Steven Tyler.
He did?
Yes to what?
Uh, he said I have a good
voice for American idol.
He did?
I'm gonna say no.
Awesome.
He did.
Okay.
I missed that scene.
So a small misunderstanding
there, but that's nothing
compared to the disconnect
between these two.
So how you guys feeling today?
A little nervous.
Excited.
This sucks.
My name is chelsee oaks.
I'm 23, and I'm from
Nashville, Tennessee.
My name is rob bolin, I'm 23, and
I'm from Nashville, Tennessee.
And...We're exes.
The first day that rob and I met, he
asked me up onstage to sing with him.
So we've been singing together
literally since the day that we met.
We just sort of...Clicked.
You guys...You were together
and you broke up, and you
auditioned for idol at the same
time, knowing that you were
gonna see each other possibly
if you made it and also compete
in the same competition if
you made it to Hollywood?
We still lived together
after we broke up.
That's not a good idea.
Did you date other people
while he was living with you?
Yeah.
All right.
♪ You don't know ♪
♪ what it's like ♪
That's so uncool.
For a while there, we were
talking and getting back on good
terms and, uh...
It's turned opposite now and gone sour.
Are you friends?
Uh...At this point, not really.
But it'll...
In time it'll work out.
So you guys know I'm
a hopeless romantic.
There's no way to fix
this whole thing?
We can't get it together?
We can't make it happen?
Three years, and you duet?
We love each other very much,
and it will always be that way
for the rest of our lives.
I mean, honestly, we have
something together, but we
tried and we tried and we tried,
and it just didn't work out.
Steven, do something!
Wow, man.
Rob, is that the way
you feel as well?
Rob is so in love with her.
Little bit different, but...
How do you feel, rob?
It sucks.
Wouldn't be doing my job if I
didn't ask how this all went
down, how this all happened.
What's that?
I mean... were you the
reason for the breakup?
No, I was not the
reason for the breakup.
They broke up, you know, we met.
You know, I didn't rob before.
I really don't know him now, so...
Sing something together first.
Come on.
♪ Baby, you don't know ♪
♪ what it's like ♪
♪ baby, you don't know ♪
♪ to love somebody ♪
♪ the way I love you ♪
Oh, please.
You guys are killing
me right now.
You guys are killing me, man.
You were one voice.
You know, sometimes the deepest
passion comes from friction,
and you know, um...
I saw how much in love you were.
You're in sync.
Let's hear you separately once.
Okay. I'm gonna stand here.
You first. Yeah.
♪ Oh, mother, mother ♪
Mm.
♪ There's too many of you ♪
♪ crying ♪
♪ ooh, brother, brother ♪
♪ brother ♪
♪ there's far too many of you ♪
♪ dying ♪
Love his voice.
♪ You know ♪
♪ we've got to find a way ♪
♪ to bring some lovin' ♪
♪ here today ♪
Okay. Now it's your turn.
Now it's your turn, chelsee.
This makes me feel a lot better.
You can stand over there.
♪ All of these lines ♪
♪ across my face ♪
♪ tell you the story ♪
♪ of who I am ♪
♪ so many stories ♪
♪ of where I've been ♪
♪ and how I got to ♪
♪ where I am ♪
Okay.
Nice.
Come on back up.
Do you know what I love is that
you guys both sang well with all
the emotions that are
going on up there.
I agree.
And as beautiful as you both
sing separately...You sing
really beautifully together.
Thank you.
Your harmony together
was so deep.
So let's vote.
Uh...I'm gonna say
yes to both of you.
I think that you both have
very interesting big voices.
Thank you.
I say yes to both of you too.
And I say yes to both of you, and
guess what you're both doing?
You're both going to Hollywood.
♪ It's a quarter after one ♪
♪ I'm all alone ♪
♪ and I need you now ♪
Get outta here and fall in love
with each other all over again.
She's going to Hollywood!
Hey.
Hey!
Love goes to Hollywood.
They're gonna
get back together.
They'd better.
Have you met?
Yeah.
Yeah. Come on, give him
a congratulations.
There you go.
Where do we go from here?
Uh... Hollywood.
Hollywood.
There we go, all right.
That was, uh...
That worked out pretty cool.
We wish you luck, and
we wish you luck.
Thank you so much.
Thanks, all.
See you later.
Nice to meet you guys.
Whew! Break?
I think so.
Over the next hour...
The judges and music city continue
to be in perfect harmony.
Yes!
Best we've seen today.
You are going to Hollywood!
But later, Nashville
hits a sour note.
Reeee, reeee, reee!
♪ there goes ♪
♪ my life ♪
♪ there goes my future ♪
Welcome back to music city.
It's 10:00 A.M., and American
idol has taken over Nashville's
main drag, Broadway...
Where more than 17,000 have packed the
streets to audition.
And back inside the ryman,
things are starting to get
interesting, to say the least.
Oh, I like it, Randy.
I can touch my
tongue to my nose.
Ah!
Would you like to see it?
Sure.
Okay.
That's it.
I say yes!
Whoa, whoa.
Whaah!
Waah, waah, waah!
Nashville's bringing out the
animal in Steven Tyler.
Whoo!
And the same can be
said for this guy.
Get, cow, come on, cow!
Move on, cow, move on, cow!
Come on back here!
My name's Alan Lewis.
I'm 26 from Franklin
furnace, Ohio.
I'm a tattoo artist and many
other things at the same time.
Yeah!
So by the looks of you,
you're a pop singer.
You know it.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
My whole life, I been told, no, Lewis,
he's got his head in the clouds.
Yeah, you're good, but you're
never gonna do nothin' with it.
But you know what, man?
You continue to try.
We fight in this life for
everything that we got.
We're warriors, man.
So did someone tell
you you could sing?
I mean, I been hearing this my
whole life... "hey, man, go try
American idol," and I was like,
man, ain't that all pop and
stuff... nothin' against you.
Nothing against you.
Everyone's got their own
flavor of ice cream.
That's right.
So, you know, mine's vanilla, I
guess, and yours may be chocolate.
You know, but...
Okay, baby, well, what are you gonna sing?
I'm gonna sing
skynard's simple man.
Mm...
And, uh, on your cue and I'll sing.
Let's get it.
♪ Well, mama told me ♪
♪ when I was young ♪
♪ "sit here beside me ♪
♪ "my only son ♪
♪ "you'll find a woman ♪
♪ "yeah, baby ♪
♪ and you'll find love" ♪
♪ "There is a someone ♪
♪ "up above ♪
♪ "and be a simple ♪
♪ "kind of man ♪
♪ "oh, be somethin', child ♪
♪ you love and understand"... ♪
Whoa, okay.
You caught me.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
When you yell at my voice,
you messed me up, too.
You've got one of the best
laughs I've ever seen.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
You know...
We're all just who we are.
That's right.
I feel like you're really more...
Of a band guy, right?
I guess...ln your point of view.
You know, if you
look it that way.
I mean, like I said, my point of view...
Love criticism.
Because if you tell me, "no, I'm
not feeling you," so that's just
gonna make me go home and
practice... work harder.
Ten times harder
than what I was.
That's good.
You know, the greatest
musicians of all time have
failed their auditions
once or twice in life.
All of us have.
That happens.
Good stuff.
Yeah. There's a reason for
everything in this life.
Oh, yeah, 100%!
100%.
All right.
Good luck to you.
Thank you very much.
You guys have a good day.
We enjoyed you, man.
He came in here, the toughest
guy in the world, and then he
left here like...Philosophizing.
Like he's so humble.
So you're saying we took an untamed tiger...
And turned it into a baby.
Yes.
Oh, okay.
Good luck.
I hope everything
works out for you.
Yep.
See you.
Nice to meet you.
So the judges have tamed the beast...
But are they ready for this beauty?
My name is stormi henley.
I am 19 years old, and I am
from crossville, Tennessee.
I was miss teen usa 2009.
My boss was Donald trump.
It was really nerve-racking
being on the stage.
And I think after knowing that I
could win that competition and
perform in front of so many
people, it's really given me the
confidence to come here.
I really want to see how far
I can make it on my talent.
Uh-oh!
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh ♪
Wow!
Hi.
Hello.
What's your name?
Stormi.
No!
It's weird, isn't it?
What?
That's your real name?
Yes.
It's on my birth certificate.
Wow. I like that.
It's beautiful.
You look like you could
be miss something.
I was miss teen usa.
You're reading that!
I'm reading it.
You're cute.
What are you gonna sing?
Father, can you hear me?
Okay.
♪ Father, you know we need it ♪
♪ I've never seen so much pain ♪
♪ father, you know we need it ♪
♪ there's no more heart ♪
♪ of stone ♪
♪ we're ready for your power ♪
♪ now the sin is gone, father ♪
Mm.
You got a beautiful...
Little tight squeaky little voice, you know?
You ever throw it out a
little harder than that?
I don't.
I never have.
You never let loose?
Mm-mm.
Well, all right.
Is there singing in this competitive
thing with miss teen usa?
There's not a talent division.
There's no talent portion.
We're talented...
But there's not a talent division.
Whoo! All right, baby!
All right!
I feel you.
Okay.
Let's take a vote.
Let's do it.
I think with a little work
you can belt that out.
So I'm gonna say yes.
I think you're gorgeous, but the
voice is not strong enough for me.
I'm gonna say no.
It's up to Randy, but...
It's up to me?
Yes, baby.
Really?
It was just okay.
I don't know...
Okay, Randy, come on.
Wow.
Yeah!
Seriously, you two?
Seriously?
Okay, okay, okay.
Rub it in.
That might be the smallest
voice we've ever heard.
That may be.
In five cities!
But it was powerful.
I mean, she was beautiful.
America, I'm going to Hollywood!
So stormi continues
her reign as queen.
But later, someone gives
her a run for her money.
Younique.
And the emotions run high.
It's 4:00 P.M. in Nashville.
And as stormi celebrates with
gold, unfortunately, her name
describes the mood
in the judging room.
I'm gonna say not yet, no.
I'm gonna have to say
no this time too.
Definitely a no.
Definitely.
Where did it go wrong?
Everything.
But our next contestant knows that
every cloud has a silver lining.
My name is adrienne beasley.
I'm 22 years old, and I'm
from wickliffe, Kentucky.
I live on a farm.
It's a lot of hard work.
It really is.
Whoa!
My name is Freddy Simmons.
My name is carolyn Simmons.
And we are adrienne's parents.
When I was two years
old, I was adopted.
My parents, they are white.
And that was a lot different
for me, like growing up.
♪ I was lost ♪
♪ in the lanes... ♪
When we were out in public,
people would be totally like
confused what was going on.
She has fit into the family just...
Just like a hand in a glove.
I just see adrienne as
adrienne, you know?
She's just ours.
When she walked out the door
fixing to go to Nashville, I
said wherever God takes her
is gonna be fine with me.
They've helped me out so much, and I
wanna be able to, like, return that.
Like I really do.
♪ Steady as a preacher ♪
♪ free as a wee♪
♪ and couldn't wait ♪
♪ to get goin' ♪
♪ but wasn't quite ready ♪
♪ to leave ♪
♪ there's a wild wild whisper ♪
♪ blowin' in the wind ♪
♪ callin' out my name ♪
♪ like a long-lost friend ♪
♪ oh, I miss those days ♪
♪ as the years go by ♪
♪ oh, nothing's sweeter ♪
♪ than summertime ♪
♪ and American honey ♪
Mmm.
Very nice, very nice.
Thank you.
Wow, yeah!
I hear something so special in your voice...
And I can't put my
finger on it right now, but
it's something special.
Thank you.
Yeah. Nothin' was put on.
You nailed the chorus.
You almost made me cry.
I mean, I wasn't sure why.
There was something in your
voice that's so special.
You hold that real... hold
that close to you.
You really surprised me
there in the middle.
I really felt that.
And it sounded so good in this
ryman audororium, and this
room was built for that.
Sounded good.
I was like, yeah, all right!
Use that room, girl, go for it!
Thank you very much.
I'm gonna say yes.
I guess you're going
to Hollywood.
Oh!
Yeah!
Hollywood!
Hollywood.
Thank you guys so much.
Oh, my gosh, I
wanted this so bad.
I can't believe it.
Congratulations.
You did it.
Welcome to Hollywood.
All right, thank you.
That's so great... there it is!
You didn't exist, and we didn't... when
she was singing... that's great.
Hello?
Dad, I'm going to Hollywood.
I'm going to Hollywood.
I don't know who's gonna pay my
way, but I'm goin' to Hollywood!
My world could definitely
change, but no matter what,
the farm's always been my home.
Coming up... with day one of Nashville
in the rearview mirror, can day two
stay the course?
Wo-how!
That's what 're e okoking for.
Or is another collision waiting
for us just over the rise?
Nashville has a lot
of highs and lows.
It's just an auditionbubuddy.
It's early morning in Tennessee, and the
town of Nashville is already bustling.
As people go about their everyday business,
all signs point to idol auditions.
And today the judges arrive
with huge expectations.
If Nashville brings it today
like they did yesterday, we'll
have all the winners
from this one town.
Perhaps we'll find a shining star
in 28-year-old Camille emerics.
Singing is something I've
done ever since I was small.
I ended up being our junior
regional soloist for our
hometown, and people are very
surprised when they hear me sing.
I have a huge voice, and I'm
like 5'2", and everybody's
looking at me like, "where
did that come from?"
What are you gonna
sing for us today?
Um, I'm gonna sing some sweet
thing for you from chaka Khan.
Chaka Khan.
All right.
♪ you're my heat ♪
♪ you are my fire ♪
♪ you make me weak ♪
♪ with strong desire ♪
♪ you turn me on ♪
♪ my whole life long ♪
♪ you be right ♪
♪ or be wrong ♪
Oh!
♪ I just want to ♪
♪ satisfy you ♪
♪ 'cause you're not mine ♪
♪ I can't deny it ♪
♪ don't you hear me talking ♪
♪ baby ♪
♪ love me now or ♪
♪ I'll go crazy ♪
Wow.
You know, the acoustics work...
No matter what.
Yeah, it's big up in here.
Wow, girl.
Come on, girl.
Oh, my goodness.
You know what?
You gotta go back home and
practice and get good.
No.
Yes.
Don't sing... just don't do it.
Oh, come on.
Just don't do it.
Don't do it.
Honestly, just don't do it.
Baby, that was horrible.
Loud...lt hurt.
No. I'm sure you're a nice girl.
There's many talents you have.
So is it a no for you?
Um...Let me see.
Uh...Yeah, it's a no for me.
It's a no for me too, baby.
It's a no for me too.
Go practice.
What a waste of time,
you know what I mean?
Four hours.
Oh...
It was terrible.
I'm just trying to be honest.
And for the next hour, that
honesty was downright brutal
as the search continued for
the next fresh face in music.
♪ I can't believe ♪
♪ it's happening to me ♪
♪ some people wait a lifetime ♪
♪ for a moment like this ♪
Oh, okay.
This is too much.
Help!
But there was more strange
talent to be uncovered.
♪ if I had known ♪
♪ for just one second ♪
♪ you'd be back to bother me ♪
♪ go on now, go ♪
Wow. Ooh.
♪ I sacrifice ♪
♪ and I'm sayin' ♪
♪ amen-ah ♪
♪ and I'm alive ♪
Okay!
What kind of joke is this?
You know, you really don't
have a good voice at all.
It's a no for me.
Nashville has a lot
of highs and lows.
But outside, it was mostly lows.
Any luck, man?
No.
I'm sorry about that, buddy.
Come here.
Come here, man.
It's just an audition, buddy.
Nice to meet you.
Thanks, buddy.
As I usher out the heartbroken, the
contestants waiting are certainly feeling
the pressure... no one more
so than Jackie Wilson.
I am like...Whew.
I got... I got the jitters.
But I'm... I'm gonna be okay.
I'm gonna do this.
Hello.
Hi, baby.
Hi.
What's your name?
Jackie Wilson.
Yeah. How old are you?
I am 28 years old.
Is Jackie ready?
Yes.
For years, Jackie's been ready.
Yes. Since three.
Since three years old?
Yeah.
♪ Though you don't call ♪
♪ anymore ♪
♪ I sit and wait ♪
♪ in vain ♪
♪ and I'm gonna rap on ♪
♪ your door ♪
♪ Tap on your windowpane ♪
♪ said I'm gonna ♪
♪ camp by your steps ♪
♪ until I get through to you ♪
♪ 'cause I got to change ♪
♪ your view, baby ♪
Whoo.
Yo! Yo!
Jackie's first concert.
Yo.
I cannot believe I'm
standing here right now.
Crazy, dude.
Crazy vocals.
You did it!
You did it. Crazy.
You made us clap.
What?
You were so feeling it in the
high notes and just lettin' it
out and tellin' it like it is.
You blew it out.
I say yes.
Absolutely.
Yes.
Million percent yes.
You're going to Hollywood, baby!
You did it, Jackie!
Wow.
So unassuming.
Wow-how-ah!
♪ Whoa, yeah ♪
♪ you know that you are ♪
♪ a shooting star ♪
Oh, you're her boyfriend.
Whoa, that was... that threw me.
Oh, my gosh!
I knew that threw you.
Holy cow!
That girl was unbelievable.
Amazing!
She sang that song
like she wrote it.
Just remember that when
the other people come in.
Like that's what
we're looking for.
Whoo!
Coming up, more standout performances...
As one contestant blows the
judges away.
Wow-wuh!
I think we found the one today.
Welcome back to Nashville.
Without further ado, I give you...
Well, I'll just let her tell you.
My name is latoya Moore.
I'm 26.
I'm a recording artist.
And I'm from Nashville,
Tennessee.
I do see myself as a star.
Many people will look at me, and
I don't even have to say a word.
They see the glow.
They see a glow about me.
Younique.
Latoya...[Echo] Latoya...
I'm designed to be here, and I
hope the judges see it.
Thank you, God.
You ready?
Ready!
I think they're ready.
Let's do it.
Okay. I want you to relax.
There's cameras in there.
All right.
Why, hello!
Hello.
Ooh.
Somebody's ready for
their close-up.
Yes.
Look at that smile.
My God!
What's this cd?
This is my album, and I brought
it just for you all to share.
Thank you.
Only one?
Only one.
For the three of us?
It's spread around pretty good.
You mean people took 'em.
Oh, I gave generously.
Mm!
Anyway, Steven... but I
still love you all.
It's good to see you, miss J.Lo.
Thank you.
And Randy.
And nice to meet you too.
Nice to meet you too.
♪ When I close my eyes ♪
♪ I break down and cry ♪
♪ it's all about the way you ♪
♪ love me ♪
♪ yeah-eah ♪
♪ the thought of your kiss ♪
♪ my heart can't resist ♪
♪ we fell so deep in love ♪
What song was that?
That is tamia, when
I close my eyes.
Oh.
Are you sure?
Yes.
That sounded nothing like that.
Definitely unique.
I can definitely do this.
I will be glad to choose another
song, because this has been my
dream for a long time.
Baby, the sound, the
tone is not good.
It was just... it's
almost... it's like annoying.
Eee...Reeeeeeee.
It's almost like that.
So is it no-go for me?
I really can't believe that.
Um... we're trying to keep it real,
'cause this is gonna help you, hopefully.
All right, thank you.
Okay, sweetie.
Don't forget your number there.
♪ If this world were mine ♪
♪ all that I own ♪
♪ you've been so good to me ♪
♪ if this world were ♪
♪ mi-ine ♪
Still a no.
Thank you.
You're an idiot.
What is wrong with everyone?
♪ It's all good to me ♪
So, younique... did you understand
what they were trying to say?
I guess I did.
How do you feel about
your audition?
They probably would have liked
it if I took it a little
bit slower for 'em and, um, maybe... I
think they were fine with the pace.
This town is going crazy.
Nashville's insane.
So mean!
Well, I mean...
But as the afternoon wore on,
it was the guys who finally
changed music city's tune.
♪ Wake up, Maggie ♪
♪ I think I got something ♪
♪ to say to you ♪
♪ It's late September ♪
♪ and I really should be ♪
♪ back in school ♪
Mmm, I like it.
♪ Oh, Maggie ♪
♪ I couldn't have tried ♪
♪ anymore ♪
Very nice.
♪ Things just get so crazy ♪
♪ living life gets hard to do ♪
♪ I would gladly hit the road ♪
♪ get up and go if I knew ♪
♪ that some day it would ♪
♪ lead me back to you ♪
I think you got a
really great voice.
♪ I said ♪
Oh, man!
♪ Papa was a rollin' stone ♪
♪ wherever ♪
♪ he lay his head ♪
♪ was his home ♪
♪ and when he died ♪
Oh, you got it up there.
Nice, man.
That was so good!
So good.
Thank you, Mr. Tyler.
Yes, Steven?
Yes!
Jennifer?
Oh...
That was a cheerleader yes.
100% yes.
Welcome to Hollywood.
You got three, dog!
You're gonna go to Hollywood.
You are going to Hollywood!
Love you!
That was great.
Whoo! Yeah!
That felt so good.
I don't know if it feels better for me
when someone comes out and sings...
Hi!
Tennessee was back on track.
You guys give dreams...
And you've given me one.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
But as night falls on Nashville...
Can another star emerge?
My name is Matt dillard.
I'm from cheatham county.
It's right out of Nashville.
And I'm 27 years old.
When I was growin' up, my family
decided to take in foster children.
♪ I don't know you ♪
We have special needs children.
That's something that's real
dear to our hearts and, uh...
Helping 'em have a better life.
Ooh! Give five.
My family, they've had 700 foster
children through 23 years now.
Give Nana a kiss.
We get to watch children come
from being very sick to helping
them have a full life.
♪ And take this ♪
If I make it, I'm gonna be able
to help a lot of people and
that really, uh, really inspires me a
lot to get in here and do my best.
♪ When I am down ♪
♪ and oh my soul so weary ♪
♪ when troubles come ♪
♪ and my heart burdened be ♪
♪ then I am still ♪
♪ and wait here in the silence ♪
♪ until you come ♪
♪ and rest awhile with me ♪
Started a little high on that.
I know, I know, I know.
What I do like, though, is I come in
here, you're like the country boy.
You got the hat on...
And you sing Josh groban.
And it sounds like you're from
a whole 'nother kind of thing.
I was like... I can pretty
up too, if you want me to.
I can pretty up!
I'm not trying to suck up or
anything, but I mean, Jennifer
Lopez, I'm sitting here, and
that's a little bit hard to sing
in front of...
My favorite actress and my favorite judge
and my favorite rocker.
I mean... Steven, what do
you think, man, of Matt?
I'm on the fence.
He has a very,
very pretty voice.
Randy, what do you think, man?
I'm gonna give a very small yes.
I just hope that you
don't get swallowed up.
He's saying yes.
I'm saying no.
I think that you need to
have a better audition.
Steven...Yes or no?
Whoo!
Yes!
Going from the
country to the hood.
Yeah! Let's go!
Yeah!
Coming up, the unanimous choice
for best audition in Nashville.
Yes!
You don't want to miss the first
step of her idol journey.
Welcome back to the ryman
auditorium here in Nashville,
Tennessee where there have been so
many great country music moments here.
We're trying to keep
that legacy alive.
And over the past two days,
we may have done just that.
♪ There was a dream ♪
♪ and one day I could see it ♪
But the stadium which once held
17,000 dreamers...Has only
one more who remains.
My name is Lauren alaina.
I'm 15 years old, and I'm
from rossville, Georgia.
It's fun living here.
I like it because it's kinda
simple and laid back.
I would say I'm a typical
15-year-old girl.
Ta da!
I'm always singing.
It's what I love to do, and
my family's super-supportive.
Especially my cousin holly.
She's really the reason
that I started singing.
She's like a sister to me more than a
cousin, 'cause I was raised with her.
I really looked up to holly
growing up, 'cause she's so
beautiful and it was like
my goal to be like holly.
I love you.
I love you too.
Three years ago, holly was
diagnosed with a brain tumor,
and they told her that she was
gonna have to take chemo and
radiation and that she would
lose all of her hair.
I didn't know whether or
not she was gonna live.
And I don't know what I'd do
without holly, 'cause she's my...
she's like my big sister and...
So I just tried to do as much as
I could, and I stayed with her.
I did a fundraiser.
I sang, and all the money I
got I saved up for holly.
Are you ready for the audition?
Oh, yeah, I'm ready.
I've been here all day.
I know.
You're the last one.
Get in there and good luck.
We'll be waiting for you.
Cross your fingers.
Fingers crossed.
♪ Hey, Lauren ♪
Hey, Lauren, what's going on?
Come on in.
How y'all doing?
We're good.
So your name is Lauren what?
Alaina.
And who inspired you
to come and audition?
Um, my cousin holly, actually.
Well, she's the reason I
ever started singing.
I would go over to her house and
we would go to her room and
listen to music and just sing
all the time, and she urged me
to try out, so here I am.
Right.
Do you wanna bring her in?
Holly!
I hear those footsteps.
Where are you, ho... hey!
Hello.
Come on in.
Aw, you're gonna
make me cry now.
Aw!
Whose little girl is this?
That's ours.
That's yours?
That's our baby.
You look too young
to... thank you!
Well, she looks a little bit older
probably than she is, right?
She's 15.
She'll be 16 in about two weeks.
Are you excited?
I'm about to fall over.
♪ You never looked so good ♪
♪ as you did last night ♪
♪ underneath the city lights ♪
♪ there ♪
♪ walking with your friend ♪
♪ laughing at the moon ♪
♪ I swear you looked ♪
♪ right through me ♪
♪ but I'm ♪
♪ still living with your ♪
♪ good-bye ♪
♪ and you're ♪
♪ just going on with your life ♪
♪ how can ♪
♪ you just walk on by ♪
♪ without ♪
Best we've seen today.
Wow-ah!
Best I've seen today
in Nashville.
I'm telling you, I'm blown away.
I'm sitting here like you could
have sang the whole thing.
We're just like we're
enjoying it that much.
Oh, my God!
Don't cry.
You're gonna make me cry too!
Don't cry, you're too pretty.
No crying.
You'll mess up your makeup!
Guys, we gotta give mad
props, though, to holly.
'Cause holly, you
saw something, man.
You definitely got a gift.
See, I think you should cry.
'Cause you're gonna make
40 million people cry.
Tears of joy, baby.
But I mean, you've got real
natural God-given talent.
I been saying it every season.
It doesn't matter what age,
where, what, what, what.
If you got it, you got it.
And you got it.
And you definitely got it.
One, two, three.
Yes!
You're going to Hollywood!
I can't wait to see
you there again.
Wow!
Oh, can I say one thing?
Yes.
My family's dying to meet
y'all, and I'm last.
Can I go get 'em real fast?
Yes.
She is "beyondo" cute.
Aah!
The last one of the day!
Last one of the day.
I gotta go get my family.
Oh, believe me, they're
ready for you.
She's a baby.
She's 15 years old.
Hi.
Hello, Lauren's family.
Hi!
Will you sing something
in front of your family?
My mom and dad's song
is one of yours.
Oh, yeah, sing that.
Sing that.
♪ I could stay awake ♪
♪ just to hear you breathing ♪
Whoo!
♪ Watch you smile while ♪
♪ you are sleeping ♪
Sing it!
♪ While you're far away ♪
♪ and dreamin' ♪
♪ I could spend my life ♪
♪ in this sweet surrender ♪
♪ I could stay lost ♪
♪ in this moment ♪
♪ forever ♪
What y'all think?
Dude!
Yo!
Congratulations!
That's a wrap!
♪ I close my eyes ♪
♪ I don't wanna fall asleep ♪
♪ 'cause I'd miss you, babe ♪
♪ and I don't wanna ♪
♪ miss a thing ♪
That's it for the historic
ryman in Nashville.
As we close up shop and the judges head out...
Yeah, yeah!
Great day in Nashville.
Steven has one last prediction.
I think we found the one today.
We found her.
Oh, yeah, we did. Yep.
And with that, our
road trip continues.
It's not our first time at this
rodeo, but when we hit Austin,
we're welcomed with an unlikely
kind of Southern hospitality.
Unh!
Get the [Bleep] Out of my face.
What just happened?
No matter what may transpire...
People are bringing the pain and the fire.
You're going to Hollywood.
One thing is for sure.
Whoo!
The Texas-sized talent...
I think you're awesome.
You might be one of the
best people we've seen.
Rules the roost.
Sync by Behzadt
www.addic7ed.com