It's the right room.
Texas, hot, Austin.
Jennifer, Steven, Randy.
What's your name?
Uh, my name is Jake muck.
Jake muck?
You know what "muck"
rhymes with, don't you?
"Duck"?
Read my lips.
[Upbeat techno music]
♪
Welcome to Austin!
Let's heat it up!
Whoo!
It's our third time saddling up to
take a ride here in the state capital.
Waiting to take the bull by the
longhorns were 75,000 hopefuls.
This year's batch was no different
than any other Austin cattle call.
They were a little bit country...
Hoo!
Little bit rock and roll...
Oh, yeah!
And a whole lot of weird.
[High-pitched vocalizing]
♪ We can testify ♪
And eager to get their ride in on the
Austin audition coach... come on, ginger.
[Horse whinnies]
Were our judges.
Morning.
I hear the talent here
in Austin is crazy good.
[Spits]
So we round everyone up...
To get interviewed and to soak up the experience.
This is amazing.
As the crew makes a few final
touches to the set, the judges
are ready to get
down to business.
All that was missing was me.
Okay, dad.
Love you. Bye.
I'm in Austin for idol.
Let's go, Ryan.
Work it out.
Come on, seacrest.
Parents wondering where I am.
Trying to prove to them I
actually work for a living.
So while I was wrapping up with my family...
Come say hi.
Yo.
Jennifer's husband,
Marc Anthony, took the
opportunity to spend a
little time with his.
You don't kiss me like that.
I love this town, though.
I'm working on it, though.
Working up the nerve.
I love this town.
It's important to keep
in touch with family.
♪ 'Cause it's a family ♪
♪ affair ♪
Something that our first
contestant of the day knows all
too well.
My name is Cory levoy, I'm 21
years of age, and this is my
older sister Brooks.
We didn't get to meet each other
until I was 14 and she was 16,
due to parental differences, and
we actually lived 15 minutes
away from each other
our whole lives.
And we didn't know it.
♪ I have been searching ♪
♪ all of my days ♪
After my sister and I met,
we clicked instantly.
My name's tiki.
We are most definitely
best friends.
♪ Saw a smile ♪
♪ and know I'll feel this ♪
♪ loneliness no more ♪
My brother and mine's relationship
means everything to me.
That's a little, bitty
microphone, ain't it?
Look, that's a little mini one.
My sister definitely has encouraged
me to come and audition.
I love hearing him sing.
I love seeing the looks on people's
faces whenever he performs.
I don't think that there's anybody
that supports me as much
as she does.
This is probably one of the
most exciting days of my life.
Yo.
Hi.
Hello.
How are y'all doing?
What's going on, man?
We're good.
How are you doing?
I'm doing pretty good.
How'd you get here today?
Uh, my sister.
Your sister drove you?
Yeah.
She's my best friend, actually.
Really?
Yeah, she's very supportive
of my singing career.
What if we put her on this
panel to judge with us?
What do you think she'd do?
She would probably be a little
bit more harsh than y'all are.
Wow. Get her in here.
Nice.
Where is she?
Got get her. Go get her.
Really?
Get her, dude.
She's gonna judge you with us.
You have to come
in here with me.
Bring her in.
Hello.
You have to be honest.
Okay.
I'm always honest with him.
Whoo.
I love that. Right here.
Come on, Brooks.
It sounds like you got more
nervous now that she's gonna be
judging.
Yeah.
Yeah, what you gonna
do now, dog?
What are you gonna be singing?
I'm gonna be singing I can't make
you love me by Bonnie Raitt.
Mm.
Okay.
I love that song.
[Clears throat]
♪ Lay down with me ♪
♪ and tell me no lies ♪
♪ and just hold me close ♪
♪ don't patronize ♪
♪ me ♪
♪ 'cause I can't make you ♪
♪ love me if you don't ♪
♪ you can't make your heart ♪
♪ feel something it won't ♪
Mm.
♪ 'Cause here in the dark ♪
♪ in these final hours ♪
♪ I will lay down my heart ♪
♪ and I'll feel the power ♪
♪ 'cause I can't make you ♪
♪ love me ♪
Ah.
Sorry.
Wow.
I'm pretty freakin' nervous.
Sister Brooks, what's up, man?
Have me judge?
Yes.
I think it was amazing.
[Laughter]
Wow.
♪ It's amazing ♪
He gives me chill bumps.
So does her "yes"
count for Hollywood?
No?
Well, we'll see.
Let's see. Let's see.
Maybe half a vote.
Half a vote.
Yeah.
Dude, I think you got
a good voice, man.
I was really, uh, surprised and
impressed, 'cause I didn't know...
'cause your speaking voice was so
high that I didn't know where
your singing voice
was gonna sit.
I been... kind of been teased my
whole life about how high-
pitched my voice is, but if I
didn't talk the way I talk, I
wouldn't be able to sing
the way that I sing.
Well, you're very gifted.
All the runs you were doing, so
beautiful, and you landed them
so perfectly, and it was
really, really nice.
Really nice.
Something tells me you're not
gonna get teased anymore.
I hope not.
Let's... let's start the
vote down there.
Brooks, what are you
saying, Brooks?
Heck yeah.
>>Eck yeah.
They're saying "heck yeah."
I'm gonna say "heck yeah" too.
I'm gonna say "y'all heck yeah."
All right, dog, yeah.
That's four.
Welcome to Hollywood!
I was told that I
had to say this.
My whole life, I've been told
that I have a j.Lo booty.
Heck yeah.
Well, uh... close-up of that?
Yes, I had to say it.
Little bit of swag going
back and forth there.
Wow.
Well, congratulations.
You're going to Hollywood.
We'll see you there.
See you later.
It was nice to meet y'all.
It's so funny.
Everybody uses the
term, "give it up.
Give it up."
But no one... people rarely do.
They just... that was great.
With his sister's support,
Cory is off to Hollywood.
Going to Hollywood, baby!
But the next contestant would
have to go it alone, and that
can be tough.
Hey.
Hello.
Hi.
Hi. What's your name?
Holly.
Okay, where you from?
I'm originally from liverpool,
england, but I now
live in mckinney, Texas.
And how old are you?
I'm 17.
And what do you like to sing?
What are you gonna
sing us tonight?
I'm gonna sing at
last by etta James.
All right, well, let it fly.
Let's hear it.
♪ At last ♪
♪ my love has come along ♪
♪ my lonely days are over ♪
♪ and life is like a song ♪
♪ yeah ♪
♪ but you smile ♪
Okay, thanks, holly.
Thank you.
Well, I heard the lyrics, but you
were all over the place with melody.
Yeah, you switched keys
about five times there.
Tough song to sing.
Yeah, I feel like if you let it out,
we could get a little bit more of you.
And it's the kind of thing where
maybe you need to just get
a little bit more
comfortable on stage.
Mm-hmm.
Randy?
Sorry.
It's okay.
Yeah, you're not quite
ready yet, love.
I'm gonna say no.
Was your daughter excited
about this today?
Yeah.
Very.
To the extent that she's really
nervous now, so... yeah.
Yeah.
The nervousness actually can
help sometimes, can't it?
I hope so.
Can you do my a favor?
You think you can collect yourself to
sing one more song, one more chance?
After the break, find out if
holly survives the first cut.
Hate to say no to you, but...
Plus, the auditions get a visit from a legend.
This is John Wayne.
My name is John Wayne schulz.
John Wayne. Come on.
As Austin shows us
the cowboy way.
♪ Leave me if you need to ♪
It's not going good in Austin.
Welcome back to Austin.
Before the break, holly's
nerves got the best of her.
You okay?
She's really nervous now, so...
Yeah.
The nervousness actually can
help sometimes, can't it?
I hope so.
And now the judges are giving her a
second chance to make a first impression.
Can you do me a favor?
You think you can collect yourself to
sing one more song, one more chance?
But Randy has already said no.
♪ I can almost see it ♪
♪ that dream I'm dreaming ♪
♪ but there's a voice ♪
♪ inside my head ♪
♪ saying you'll never reach it ♪
♪ every step I'm taking ♪
♪ every move I make ♪
♪ feels lost with no direction ♪
♪ my faith is shaking ♪
Mm.
♪ But I ♪
♪ I got to keep trying ♪
♪ got to keep my head ♪
♪ held high ♪
♪ it's always gonna be ♪
♪ another mountain ♪
♪ I'm always gonna wanna ♪
♪ make it move ♪
♪ always gonna be ♪
♪ an uphill battle ♪
♪ ain't about what's waiting ♪
♪ on the other side ♪
You believe that song?
Yeah.
That was so much better.
Really good.
It was so much better.
I'm gonna say yes.
Thank you.
Steven?
I'm gonna say yes too.
Thank you.
And guess what.
I'm gonna completely
reverse my feel.
I'm gonna say yes too.
That was good.
Yo.
You nailed it.
That was really great.
Steven, where's this
young girl going?
You're going to Hollywood!
Yes.
Holly successfully makes the climb
to keep her idol dreams alive.
She made it.
Yes!
High five.
Good one, team.
♪ I believe she believed ♪
It's an emotional roller
coaster for holly, but now she
can shed some tears of joy.
I'm going to Hollywood!
Whoo!
But as the day pushes on, the tears
begin to come in the form of heartache.
Know you're trying to make it
your own, but I think you need
a little bit more time.
I'm gonna say no.
Sorry.
As the pain of rejection sinks in...
I've failed everybody.
And the contestants leave their
big dreams behind in Texas.
The voice is just
not strong enough.
I didn't hear the "it" that
we're looking for here.
We love you, son.
We love you.
I'm just not what
they're looking for.
After that rough patch, the judges
are eager to see some real talent.
Waiting.
Waiting for the next American
idol to walk through the door.
Hi.
Hey.
Okay, so what are
you gonna sing?
Uh, the circle of life.
Okay.
♪ The circle of life ♪
♪ and it moves your soul ♪
♪ to carry and hold ♪
♪ through faith and love ♪
♪ the circle of life ♪
Oh. Sorry.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Yeah, this is not going the way
you... I'm sure you were thinking.
This is not... it's just not good.
Yeah.
You have a vibrato, but
basically, it's so out of tune
and there's no melody.
The singing, honestly,
was terrible.
So it's a no, right?
Uh, yeah, it's a no for today.
All right.
Aw!
♪ It's a hard world ♪
It's all right.
I will take it.
You're stupid!
You're so stupid!
So sweet.
Well, if sweet doesn't get you
any votes, maybe the judges
are looking for something
a little more rugged.
Good thing we came
to cowboy country.
Been singing most of my life.
Um, good or bad, I just
let it out there.
[Beat boxing]
♪ When daddy hang up ♪
♪ she was gone again ♪
♪ leave me if you need to ♪
Okay.
All right.
Thanks, dog.
[Clears throat]
The problem has been finding
cowboys who can sing.
They said no.
They said I wasn't ready.
They said I needed to
work on my performance.
It looked like our hopes of
finding an authentic cowboy...
Completely and utterly
heterosexual.
Just want to throw
that out there.
Who can sing would fall on the
shoulders of the Duke of them all.
So why did you name
him John Wayne?
He wanted a son that
was rough and tough.
Would have really sucked
if I were your son, huh?
No.
No, you're... you wouldn't be the
way you are now, my friend.
Aw!
Whoa, let's go!
My name is John Wayne schulz.
I'm 23 years old, and I'm from
karnes city, Texas, and I work
on a ranch.
Back in 1857, my family came to
Texas and ranched cattle, and so
cowboys in my family goes back a
long time, and I think it's in
our blood.
We have a cattle ranch
of about 800 acres.
We've got several
head of cattle.
To me, being an authentic cowboy
is not so much how you dress.
It's more about who
you are inside.
Oh, I come from such
a wonderful family.
And I couldn't imagine doing
anything in life without my family.
In 2007, my mother was diagnosed
with breast cancer, and it...
I mean, it was a hard time for all
of us, and I told her, "mom,
I love you.
I'll do anything for you."
And she said, "well, try
out for American idol."
I just feel that he has such a
voice and a talent to share
with so many people.
And he's so genuine.
He is the most genuine, kindest
person you'd ever meet.
And he loves his mama.
Three years later, she's... she's
still here, and... and I'm
hoping I'm fulfilling that
promise to her today.
Hi.
Come on in, cowboy.
How are you?
I'm great.
What's your name, man?
John Wayne schulz.
John Wayne?
Come on. Really?
Yes, sir.
Swear?
How old are you, John Wayne?
23.
23. And where you from?
I'm from karnes city, Texas.
Kind of like a little cow town.
So you rope, you do everything.
Yes, sir.
So you're a real cowboy.
I hope so.
So why are you here today?
What brings you here to idol?
Today I'm gonna fulfill a promise
that I made to my mother.
So this is for mom and you?
Yes, sir, this is
my... this is my dream.
What are you gonna sing?
I'm gonna sing believe
by Brooks & Dunn.
Great song. Do it.
Okay.
♪ I can't quote the book ♪
♪ the chapter or the verse ♪
♪ but I know that it don't end ♪
♪ with a slow ride in a hearse ♪
It's great to see, um...
A show like this... I can hear him.
A show like this that... that
gives opportunity for just your
small-town kiddo a chance.
♪ I raise my hands ♪
♪ bow my head ♪
♪ and tell me that ♪
♪ there's more to life ♪
♪ than just what I can see ♪
♪ ho I believe ♪
♪ ho I ♪
♪ I believe ♪
All right. Great.
Great.
That last "believe" almost
brought a tear to my eye.
Mm-hmm.
I believed that you believed.
[Laughter]
You have the strength of
faith, and I can feel that.
And it comes out
in your singing.
Thank you.
Steven, what do you think?
Beautiful.
Uh, great. I liked it.
Yeah, I really, uh...
I feel... I feel you, man.
I get you. I really like it.
I think you could do well.
Thanks.
Where are the parents?
They're outside waiting.
Can you bring 'em in?
Yes, sir.
We want to tell 'em.
Grab 'em.
Okay.
You two. You two. Go in.
Go on in. Go in.
Open the door.
Okay.
Hi.
Hi, the parents of John Wayne.
Man, I been waiting to meet you.
Good to meet ya.
Can we tell 'em all together?
Short and straight
and damn straight.
So, listen, we've got something... some
good news for your son here.
I hope so.
So, guys, what are we saying to
this lovely, talented, young man?
All: Welcome to Hollywood!
Whoo!
You made it.
You made it. You made it.
♪ I hope the days come easy ♪
♪ and the moments pass slow ♪
I'm excited.
I don't think America will
be disappointed in him.
No, you know what?
He's a genuine, really nice guy.
We felt his whole
spirit, his passion.
You guys raised a good boy.
Thank you, thank you.
Congratulations.
Yeah.
Thank you so much and
nice to meet you.
Nice to meet y'all.
Where's your ticket?
You don't have a ticket.
It's right out outside...
They're gonna give it to him outside!
Right outside.
Nice.
♪ My wish for you ♪
♪ is that this life becomes... ♪
I'm just grateful that I was
able to fulfill my promise to my
mom, and... and it was a neat
experience for us to be able to
hold the gold ticket together.
♪ I hope you know ♪
♪ somebody loves you ♪
So tell my mom thank you so much
for all of your love and support.
We finally found our cowboy, but
it didn't come without a price.
I don't know how that happens, but
we have, uh, belt buckle damage.
That's gonna leave a mark.
We're going to Hollywood!
Whoo!
It seems John Wayne left
quite the impression.
It's taken Texas
up a notch for me.
Yes.
Now I'm looking
forward to tomorrow.
Coming up, it's day two
of the Austin auditions.
Whoo!
Is there more Texas
talent to be rustled up?
I loved everything I heard.
You really brought
a tear to my eye.
Or should Austin be
put out to pasture?
[Singing off-key]
My true love finds me.
Ryan seacrest is the
sexiest man alive.
But will she be able to cluck her
way into the judges' hearts?
[Imitating chicken]
What kind of show is this?
Make me a star!
Whoo!
It's the second day here in
Austin, and today's contestants
have a tough act to follow.
Whoo!
Steven Tyler!
Oh, my God.
♪ Until we meet again ♪
The boys were in a good mood, and made
time for a hard-hitting interview.
Oh, careful.
Didn't mean to hit you.
Was I nervous doing this?
You bet your booty.
And talking about
Jennifer anyway.
Um... and she arrived
glammed up and good to go.
Wow.
You've never seen me
with red lipstick?
A vision of loveliness.
No, not like that.
Look at you.
Anyone that can do that to her
face, like, pull it back like
this, is just gorgeous.
The judges took their seats,
ready to be wowed by the talent.
See if we can rev it up, baby.
Let's rev it up.
I'm ready.
But our first contestant, Courtney penri,
was more concerned with impressing
someone else.
Ryan seacrest is the
sexiest man alive.
Like, he's amazing.
He's over there.
♪ I've been alone with you ♪
♪ inside my mind ♪
I've been dreaming about
this day forever.
♪ And in my dreams ♪
♪ I've kissed your lips ♪
♪ a thousand times ♪
I will marry him someday.
♪ Hello ♪
I really can't wait to meet him.
Hopefully I won't make
a fool out of myself.
[Laughs]
Are you all right?
What's wrong?
I'm just so excited to meet you.
You're not... you're not crying
'cause you're meeting me.
You're... really?
I... thank you.
♪ And my arms are open wide ♪
Ryan seacrest will
be mine someday.
You know you love me.
Because I love you, and
I've loved you forever.
♪ And I want to tell you ♪
♪ so much ♪
I'm sorry.
♪ I love you ♪
Hey, what's going on, Courtney?
What's up?
How old are you?
I'm 17.
You're beautiful.
I'm sorry.
I just had to get that...
Thank you.
I mean, I showered and shaved...
Randy, one time, can you just
let the compliment
sit... oh, yeah.
Jennifer you meant. Yes.
Can I soak up one... the
nice thing they say to me?
Okay.
It's not all the time.
You too, Randy.
Thank you... I... yeah.
I... I wasn't doing it for that, but...
If you must.
Okay, yes. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Anything interesting we
should know about you?
Yes, I can do a chicken.
Would you like to see it?
Yes.
This is for my
friends back home.
[Imitating chicken]
[Laughter]
What kind of show is this?
What are you gonna sing?
Uh, stay by sugarland.
Okay.
Go for it.
♪ Baby, why don't you stay ♪
♪ I'm down on my knees ♪
♪ I'm so tired of being lonely ♪
♪ don't I give you ♪
♪ what you need ♪
♪ if she calls you to go ♪
♪ there is one thing ♪
♪ you should know ♪
♪ I can take another minute ♪
♪ after all that I put in it ♪
Okay.
There was parts of your voice
that are really strong, and then
there's parts that have some
weaknesses in it, you know?
I mean, as a total
package, I love you.
Uh-huh.
And I think there needs to be a
little work done on those weaknesses.
Steven, what'd you think?
I think you got star quality.
Yup.
We got to, you know, kindle
this up some, but I liked it.
Thank you.
Yeah, I thought you have
a pretty good voice.
There's a couple little bad habits in
there that you need to probably break.
Okay.
Uh, let's take a vote.
Steven, yes or no?
Yes.
It's a no for me.
Jennifer?
Uh... I'm gonna say yes for you.
The two of them says yes, so that
means you're through to Hollywood!
Aah!
That's my victory dance.
Yeah.
Aw, yeah.
Back it up, girl.
Back it up.
See?
It's the chicken.
There it is.
[Imitating chicken]
Bring more of that
when you perform.
That's it.
Whatever.
I still love you, Randy.
Bring more of that into your
performance, Ryan seacrest.
Bring more of that in
your performance, Ryan.
Congratulations.
Good job.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's all right.
Aw.
Were they hard on you?
Psyche.
And true to Austin's nature,
Courtney gets the day off to
a weird but wonderful start.
We're going to Hollywood!
When we come back, Austin
delivers Texas-size talent.
You're just a natural.
I think you're awesome.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes for me.
And love survived
the audition room.
You guys a...Couple?
Yeah.
We are.
Aw, this is love.
Plus, the dog messes with Texas.
Is there a song called
watch me leave?
Next.
And Texas bites back.
[Bleep] Out of my face.
Welcome back to the
lone star state!
Whoo!
Where Texas pride
is alive and well.
Whoo!
Austin, Texas.
Home of the best
barbecue in the world.
Home of the Texas longhorns.
Whoo!
Back in the room, the contestants were
giving the judges a reason to feel that
same pride.
♪ And this house just ain't ♪
♪ no home ♪
♪ any time he goes away ♪
♪ but oh a chair ♪
♪ is not a house no ♪
♪ but I'm gonna break ♪
♪ I'm gonna break my ♪
♪ I'm gonna break my rusty ♪
♪ cage ♪
You're just a natural.
But, man, I heard you nail notes and hit
notes, and your passion was beautiful.
I think you're awesome.
You might be one of the
best people we've seen.
It's a yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes for me.
It's a million percent yes from me
too, so you're going to Hollywood!
Yes!
You did it!
Once the talent had gained momentum...
There was no stopping it.
It's a good morning
here in Austin, Texas.
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Yeah!
I'm going to Hollywood, baby!
Day two became a party, and
the judges were loving it.
Where is your pitchfork,
you little devil?
Oh, wow.
What do you do for a living?
Clinical trials for, like,
pharmaceutical companies.
We have something in common.
That's pretty much the
whole '70s for me.
Yeah, American idol.
Going to Hollywood.
What?
There something in the coffee
out there this morning?
I know, man.
What is going on?
People coming ready for us.
It's crazy.
I'm going to Hollywood!
Whoo!
Wow.
[Bleep] Great day.
Holy [Bleep].
Everyone after another...
Vibes are great.
One after another.
Really great.
There was definitely a bond
forming between the judges and
the contestants.
You could say it's a bit of a
love fest, but that's nothing
compared to this.
Watch.
♪ One look in your eyes ♪
I'm jacqueline dunford.
I'm 22 years old.
I'm from scottsdale, Arizona.
I'm Nick fink.
I'm 19, and I'm also from
scottsdale, Arizona.
He's my boyfriend.
And she is my girlfriend.
♪ Here in my heart ♪
We met in choir at our
community college.
We had a duet together, and we
just really connected, you know?
♪ Here and now ♪
So we're just not, like,
an average couple.
I just like to think of
Nick being me in boy form.
Like, everything I like to do and,
like, my mannerisms, like,
it's not that I'm in
love with myself.
♪ Here and now ♪
We're kind of setting out to be
American idol's first power couple.
For us to actually be here and get
the opportunity, that's huge.
This is really what we would love
to do with our lives, you know?
Oh.
Hi.
Oh, here they are.
How are you?
Are you guys a couple?
Yeah.
We are.
Oh, this is love.
American idol style.
They're bashful.
Look at 'em.
Like... who's going first, Nick?
Want to take it?
I'll take it away.
Ladies first?
Yeah, oh, I like it.
Okay.
♪ Well I love you ♪
♪ but I got to stay true ♪
♪ my morals got me on my knees ♪
♪ I'm begging please ♪
♪ stop playing games ♪
♪ well I don't know ♪
♪ what you do ♪
♪ but you do it well ♪
♪ I'm under your spell ♪
♪ you got me begging you ♪
♪ for mercy ♪
♪ ooh hoo ♪
♪ why don't you release me ♪
♪ you got me begging you ♪
♪ for mercy ♪
♪ why don't you release me ♪
Oh, sweet.
There's definitely one person in
here that loves your singing.
This guy, your boyfriend.
That's my boy.
Wow.
Uh, okay, you want to step aside,
and, Nick, you want to come up?
Yeah.
[Sighs]
Okay.
♪ Sunday morning ♪
♪ rain is falling ♪
♪ steal some cover ♪
♪ share some skin ♪
♪ the clouds are shrouding us ♪
♪ in moments unforgettable ♪
♪ you twist to fit the mold ♪
♪ that I am in ♪
Wow. Okay.
♪ That may be all I need ♪
♪ in darkness she is all I see ♪
All right, cool.
You want to come
back up, jacqueline?
You know, you both sang songs
that we hear a lot, but they
both had very interesting takes
on each of the songs, which I
really, really like.
Really good.
Both of you.
Steven, what'd you think?
Sucker for melody.
I loved your song.
Yep.
And I loved the passion you put
in yours and the way you sang.
And your gorgeous look, and
you're a beautiful looking man.
You guys are love... it's just a...
It's a beautiful thing.
Yeah, and you know what?
This was, like, a
breath of fresh air.
It was like, "yo,
what's this gonna be?"
And it was good.
Thank you, Randy.
Steven, yes or no?
I say yes for both of ya.
Jennifer, yes or no?
Yes and yes.
Oh, my God.
And I say yes and yes.
You're both going to Hollywood.
♪ I promise to love... ♪
The lovers go to Hollywood.
Thank you so much, guys.
Keep that flame alive.
Favorite couple on
idol in ten years.
♪ Here and now ♪
♪ I promise to love ♪
♪ faithfully ♪
I'm just so proud of him.
It's just an amazing opportunity, so...
Nick and jacqueline's love
got them through Austin.
Now their story will
continue in Hollywood.
Coming up, more
incredible talent.
Really, really beautiful.
So good.
And one contestant tries to prove it's
what's on the inside that counts.
Stay with us as things get wild.
Get him out of my face.
And weird in Austin.
Wow.
What just happened?
[Classical music]
Welcome back to Austin!
It's 11:45, and the good
times are still rolling.
Whoo!
Day two was turning into a good,
old-fashioned honky tonk.
And Tennessee native janelle
Arthur feels right at home.
There are some people who just
look at country people and
they... they think that we have no
teeth and that we don't wear our
shoes, but, you know, we just
have an easy-going way of
living, and we love
to play music.
We love to be together.
We love to eat good food.
My family, they have been trying
and trying to get me to do this
for five years, I guess.
I think I'm ready to go for
it and just take a chance.
♪ Don't you be wasting ♪
♪ all your money ♪
♪ on syrup and honey ♪
How are you feeling today?
Great.
Feeling great, nervous,
but for janelle.
We love her.
We know she's a star.
We just want the world to know it, and
hopefully that's what's gonna happen.
♪ I been waiting on you ♪
Okay.
You got something else?
A little up-tempo?
Yeah.
♪ Been drinking ♪
♪ stupid ♪
♪ but boy I been hit by ♪
♪ cupid ♪
♪ and no one needs to know ♪
♪ right now ♪
♪ yeah and I'm not lost ♪
♪ anymore ♪
♪ at night ♪
♪ and he don't know ♪
Okay.
I had enough. I had enough.
I had enough.
Yeah, what are we doing here?
Let's say yes or no right away.
Oh, man, that was
terribly great.
Yes?
So good.
Jennifer, yes?
Yes.
Oh, my... I say yes.
Three yeses.
You're through to Hollywood.
That was so good, girl.
So good.
Through to Hollywood.
You were great.
...So much.
Thank you.
Okay, get ready.
[Cheers and applause]
And just like that, another
golden ticket in Austin.
Yeah.
That's good.
But the winning streak
had to end sometime.
Let's do it.
Are you ready for
your next contestant?
I'm ready.
Mm.
Hi.
I'm an armadillo.
Okay, come on, armadillo.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
The arrival of a seven-foot armadillo...
How does it work?
Just un-clip it.
Signaled a turning point.
We should have put a sign on the door,
because Randy started to bare his teeth.
♪ Dog ♪
All right, I'll kick it off.
Let's go.
♪ Woof ♪
♪ this is your granddaddy ♪
♪ granddaddy, granddaddy ♪
Next.
♪ Aah... ♪
♪ to... ♪
♪ mic... ♪
♪ dog ♪
What kind of audition is this?
♪ You're gonna be popular ♪
Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry.
Can I please start over?
No, I'm good.
It was not good.
It was pitchy, all
over the place.
Pitchy?
I don't mean to laugh.
[Bleep].
It's a no today, dog.
Definite no.
It's a no. Thank you.
Randy is the new Simon.
Just give me a song.
Is there a song called
watch me leave?
Um, no?
♪ And I'm dying inside ♪
Me too.
♪ And nobody know is it ♪
♪ but me ♪
Not sure about that.
♪ Nobody knows it but me ♪
Nobody really needs
to know, I think.
It was just all kind of wrong
for me, yoknow what I mean?
I'll just be an armadillo
for the rest of my life.
[Sighs]
Good luck with things.
I...I know that I can do it, and
I know what I'm capable of, and
I wish that they...
That they would have seen it
too, so it just... it's more of me
wishing that they would have
seen the potential that
I see in myself, so...
When we come back... whoo!
The Austin auditions
come to a close.
And this guy can really blow.
Yeah.
But can he sing?
Uh-oh.
Welcome back to Austin.
We are close to wrapping
up our Texas auditions.
Really tough.
Everybody's going through.
Before the break... no ticket?
We hit a rough spot, and
the mood has changed.
Dude, don't make me slap
the [Bleep] Out of you.
Get the [Bleep] Out of my face.
Get that [Bleep]...
And it's not surprising that
some contestants would pause to
put their feelings to music.
♪ I gave it my all ♪
♪ he gave it his all ♪
♪ best I could do ♪
♪ best he could do ♪
♪ but they told me no ♪
♪ but they told him no ♪
♪ you didn't ♪
♪ make it through ♪
♪ oh, no, no, no, no, no ♪
Hoping to add some rhythm to the
blues is our last contestant.
I'm Casey Abrams.
I'm 19 year old, and I'm
from idlewild, California.
Some people actually say
that I look like Seth rogan.
I don't see it.
What... what were you thinking?
What?
This is my melodica, and it's
gonna help me stay in tune, and
it's gonna keep me from boredom.
This thing has got
me some attention.
What's happening?
Nothing.
I'm... I'm kind of psyched.
Uh, I'm kind of scared
to go last right now.
Why?
I don't know.
It just puts a lot
of pressure on me.
I feel like the
judges will be tired.
Don't you think so?
No.
Ugh.
They ramp up at happy hour.
Wow, okay.
Well, you're giving me
more confidence, man.
It's two for one night.
I'm really nervous, because
I've been seriously, like,
practicing for this
show my whole life.
I can't believe I'm
gonna be doing this.
Hey guys.
Yo.
Is that a harmonica thing?
Or is that a flashlight
to see what we're saying?
It's a flask, actually.
It's a melodica.
What's your name?
I'm Casey Abrams.
Casey, how old are you?
I'm 19.
What are you gonna sing?
I'm gonna sing I don't need
no doctor by ray Charles.
Let's hear it.
[Plays note]
[Scats]
Ungh.
♪ I don't get no doctor yeah ♪
♪ 'cause I know ♪
♪ what's ailing me ♪
♪ 'cause I know what's ♪
♪ ailing me ♪
♪ I don't need no doctor ♪
♪ tell you now ♪
♪ 'cause I know what's ♪
♪ ailing me ♪
[Scats]
♪ Ooh ♪
Ooh!
♪ I been too long away from ♪
♪ my baby yeah ♪
♪ I'm coming down ♪
♪ with the misery ♪
♪ I don't need no doctor ♪
♪ my prescription's ♪
♪ been filled ♪
♪ oh yeah ♪
♪ I been too long ♪
♪ away from my baby yeah ♪
♪ I'm coming down ♪
♪ with the misery ♪
All right, all right, all
right, yo, yo, yo, yo.
All together now.
All: Yes!
You're going to Hollywood!
You're going to Hollywood.
What?
That was... that was...
That was sick good.
I want to hear you
play that now.
Just blow, man.
♪
♪ came to Austin ♪
Casey has given our panel
something to sing about.
♪
He also gets the party started.
♪ Doesn't matter ♪
Austin. Austin.
As he claims the last
golden ticket of the day.
Congratulations, brother.
Aah!
Austin, we did it.
Oh, my [Bleep].
Day two auditions ended just
golden as they began, as 27
other contestants made
their way to Hollywood.
Welcome to Hollywood.
It's that way.
Got that gold ticket.
Here's my ticket.
♪ Like it's 2012 ♪
Welcome to... all: Hollywood!
Grandma, it's me. Hi.
I just got out of my audition.
No, I... [Laughter]
All right, you're going that way,
they're going to their cars.
We'll see you at the next stop.
Full on, though.
Great day. Great day.
Amazing day.
So many amazing people.
Tomorrow night...
[People cheering]
In the entertainment capital of the world...
L.A., baby!
I think this is gonna be big.
Let's go L.A.!
Thousands will fight...
Steven, take the microphone!
For an impossible dream.
I ain't gonna stop till I've
reached the number one spot.
Let it go.
And only one thing
stands in their way.
Mm-mm-mm.
Should've sharpened it
up before you got here.
Tune in when idol hits...
It's on.
Los Angeles.
♪ Everybody talking about ♪
Sync by Behzadt
www.addic7ed.com