The first round was hell.
Sorry to put you through this.
Over 150 contestants were
sent packing in the biggest
Hollywood week elimination ever.
I just want to sing some more.
I'm sorry.
I wanted it so bad.
One...Shot.
I lost it.
But that's nothing compared to the
challenge they're about to endure tonight.
Those who have survived are about
to face their biggest test yet.
I don't have a group.
No.
Groups.
I'm so sorry.
It has always been the most
intense part of the week.
This is not a game to me.
See? You know what?
This group is fired.
They're not here.
I don't do groups!
But this year, it's even worse.
Oh, my God.
Personalities clash.
Get out of here.
Frustrations run deep.
I'm trying.
He left us?
And it all explodes onstage.
End of the road.
I hate this.
New stars will shine...
You all made it!
And your favorite talent
will blow you away.
They gave the performance
of their life!
Get ready for group round...
If you can handle the pressure.
I don't want to be here anymore.
I just... I want to go home.
[Upbeat techno music]
♪
It's 8:30 P.M.
at the Pasadena civic auditorium.
168 contestants have just survived
the brutal cuts of day one and two.
[Squeals]
It's a huge accomplishment and
a relief to make it this far.
Round one down.
On to the groups, where we
will take over the world!
But before they can even catch
their collective breaths,
they are thrust right
back into the fire.
Right now, all of them must
form into groups as quickly as
possible because they have only
one night to pick and learn a
song from a list of 20, devise
choreography, and rehearse till
they get it right.
Oh, wow, it's still... it's
still a little rusty.
Tomorrow morning, they will
perform their routine for the
judges and face elimination
if they get it wrong.
Group round is notorious for
being the toughest part of
Hollywood week, and these
contestants know all about it.
Or at least they think they do.
You see, as soon as the day one
contestants made it through the
first round, they started
forming groups, so many of them
have been planning and
rehearsing their routines all
day, thinking they were getting
ahead of the game... that is,
until they got a little surprise.
Your group must be a mixture of
day one and day two contestants.
It has to be fair.
So now, all those well-laid plans
are laid to rest, and it's
creating chaos in the theater.
Day one, day one, day
one, day one, anybody.
We need day one.
Day two boy, over here.
We're desperate.
We're looking for
another day two person.
The group with Denise Jackson
and Brett loewenstern had been
searching and thought they had finally
found their day two member...
We found him.
Until he wandered off and joined another
group when they weren't looking.
That guy just left our group.
My group.
Whoo-hoo!
He left us?
Yeah.
Let's go on to another song.
He left.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
After a last desperate plea by Denise...
Anyone.
Austin contestant Jessica yance
steps in to fill the void.
Oh, I got some good vibes.
Hey, we're vibing.
Oh, my gosh, we are.
And the newly-formed sugar
mamas are now official.
Meanwhile, new Jersey contestant
Tiffany rios is also in the
market for a group, but she made
a comment in the first round
that didn't earn her many fans.
I'm gonna be honest.
I'm tired of seeing people
try to do what I know I can.
Huh?
Whoa.
I actually could probably go
to any group right now and
go into it, but I
want to scope first.
Four guys?
Yeah.
Do you want a girl?
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm not gonna be that person.
You will.
I'm the only professional
choreographer in this place, and
no one wants to have me?
No.
Are you being serious?
Yeah, I'm being serious.
Maybe it's a huge protest against
Tiffany from new Jersey.
Ow!
Milwaukee contestant Scotty
mccreery has yet to settle on a
group, and Tiffany tries to
convince him to join forces.
No.
Oh, you didn't get to hear me.
Like, uh, like, uh, like you're
the prize and I'm the seconds?
You sing for me.
I don't really need
this right now.
♪ I wish you could sing ♪
♪ the way you kiss ♪
♪ ooh, I love watching you ♪
♪ baby ♪
♪ when you're driving me crazy ♪
All right, all right.
We'll do it.
We'll do this.
I don't know, I don't know.
Let me go... let me go talk to my group
over here again and I'll be back.
Have fun.
Honestly.
I just want to... I just want to
see what they think, 'cause
they're all three pop people.
I just want to make sure
of what's going on.
She's crazy.
I'm being honest.
I'm trying to get
to the next round.
So Scotty will
continue his search.
But desperate and running out of
time, Tiffany decides she must
take drastic measures, and she
makes a beeline to the newest
member of the sugar
mamas, Jessica yance.
Tiffany convinces Jessica
to bail on her new friends.
And she's hot.
I love hot people.
And now the two girls just need
to find one more person to
have the minimum
three for a group.
But that leaves the sur mamas
once again incomplete.
I don't want to be that bad person who
takes somebody from another person.
We gotta shine, and if we need a
day two person, we're gonna shine.
But now the sugar mamas spy Scotty
mccreery and quickly try to nab him up.
Hey, do you want to
be in our group?
Mercy.
We're singing mercy.
No, but I just...
Oh, you're nice.
No, I just... Why do I
gotta be the one person?
We need another group
member from day two.
Are you free?
What do y'all got?
I just want to hear
what you've got.
Mercy.
♪ You got me begging you ♪
♪ for mercy ♪
♪ ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ why won't you release me? ♪
Oh, he just like...
Oh, you know what?
Forget him.
[Overlapping chatter]
Then Scotty finds Jordan dorsey's group,
whicis looking for a day two member.
But this time, it's
Scotty who's auditioning.
Are you a number two?
What?
I'm day two.
Okay.
All right, sing something.
Sing.
Like, what do you want me to sing?
I'm country.
No, you just sing a... sing a song.
Just sing a song.
♪ Baby, lock them doors ♪
♪ and turn the light... ♪
No, no, no.
Well, I can sing... ♪ someday ♪
♪ when I'm awfully low ♪
I-I feel you, hey.
All right, brah, you don't
want me in the group.
That's cool with me, brah.
I mean, fine.
We have a group
established already.
Jordan dorsey, Erica schiff,
Adrian Michael, and Lauren
Turner already had a working
foursome from day one.
It's just killing me because we
already had a group, and now
we have to add
somebody from day two.
And Jordan has set
the bar very high.
♪ I see you ♪
♪ drivin' downtown ♪
♪ with a girl I know ♪
No, no.
I mean, we're all strong.
We have one weak link.
I'm not calling you a weak link.
I'm really not.
I'm just not really
gonna let it get to me.
No one seems to work for
Jordan until they find Shane
golden, a straggler
desperate to find a group.
Here, I'll just sing a
little bit of something.
Yeah.
♪ The first time ♪
♪ I fell in love ♪
♪ was long ago ♪
♪ everything I've learned ♪
I love him, I love him!
♪ Now it's finally my turn ♪
This is my group now.
It's 10:15, and this troupe is
finally ready to take flight.
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
But many others are scrambling
to just get off the ground.
Tiffany and Jessica take the mic
in an attempt to turn their
twosome into a threesome.
Does anyone want to
be in our group?
Show of hands, please.
No.
And no one seems interested.
Oh, lord.
All right.
Scotty mccreery's search
is becoming futile.
We already have five people.
Yeah, we... and the sugar
mamas are losing hope.
It's very intense, 'cause we
had everything planned out
already, and it's like, just
everything's falling apart.
But more importantly, they're
all wasting precious time while
their competition
is well on its way.
[Laughs]
No, that's perfect.
That's perfect.
All right, what kind of dance
are you guys talking about?
I'm not... I'm not no
dadgum Michael Jackson.
Anybody?
A show of hands, up here.
♪ It's my name ♪
♪ and I'm that [lndistinct] ♪
♪ so move your bags ♪
♪ and I'll call you a cab ♪
Coming up, over the next two
hours, emotions boil over...
You've got to catch up, love.
I'm trying!
As the dreaded group
night takes its toll.
I want to go home.
But when they finally hit the stage...
[Bleep]!
Prepare yourself for the heartbreak...
Stop, stop, stop.
And the devastation.
We're gonna have to say no.
But hold on for some of the most
incredible group performances... ♪ ahhh ♪
We've ever seen.
Whoo!
It's all going down
after the break.
I want to see that again.
[Upbeat techno music]
♪
Welcome back.
It's 10:30 P.M.
The pandemonium of forming
groups with both day one and day
two contestants is well underway.
A little bit of trouble, trying
to figure out this group stuff.
We were talking to somebody
and they just got nabbed up.
And Scotty mccreery is still
searching for the right fit.
♪ I never met a girl ♪
And that's probably
how I'll do it.
Hey, that's probably... oh, that... yeah,
that sounds good, though.
We can do five.
We can do five, but we've
just got to work it out.
Yeah.
He finally finds the guaps,
a foursome who chose jacee
badeaux 'cause they had to
pick up a day two contestant.
Actually, you know what?
All right, let's do this, guys.
But Clint jun gamboa isn't sure a
fifth member is the right way to go.
I have mixed emotions about this.
Now there's like these
extra two people.
I guess we're just gonna have
to work it out, however we can.
I think we can do it.
Uncertain, the guaps head off to
see if they can make it work.
Meanwhile, across the theater,
day two survivor Ashley Sullivan
becomes the newest addition to
the day one group, the hits.
They heard that I was interested in their
song, and they welcomed me in their
group.
They had good news.
Ashley's journey thus far has
been emotional, to say the least.
Aah!
I'd really love a golden ticket.
I'd really love one.
I'd really love to
go to Hollywood.
[Crying]
Congratulations.
[Cheering]
I can't believe it.
[Crying]
She's cool, calm, and collected right now,
but let's see how she copes with the
pressure tonight.
It's now 11:00 P.M.
Ready or not, group formation
chaos comes to a close,
despite desperate cries for help.
♪ How you care ♪
Tiffany rios and Jessica yance
can't find a minimum third
person to form a group.
Do you want to do a duet?
With no one willing to step up,
producers let it slide, as
39 groups head into the convention center
to prepare for the long night ahead.
If they stay up all night,
they'll have less than ten hours
to master their routines before
they sing for the judges.
♪ Back in your heart ♪
With 168 contestants
rehearsing at the same time in
the same place, peace and quiet
is almost impossible to find.
We're having a hard time hearing
each other just because
everyone else is, like,
screaming around us.
♪ Just because you ♪
It makes it much harder to
mesh around a jungle of music.
Yeah.
Some are willing to go anywhere for privacy...
I came out here in the garage
because the amount of people
and voices in there is so
overwhelming, I feel like I could
just sweat just standing there.
Even if it stinks.
♪ She knows ♪
♪ how to treat me right ♪
One of us had to go to the
bathroom, and then we decided
the acoustics in
here are so perfect.
We're in the comfort of our own
privacy in this nice, fine
bathroom, so we don't need the
comfort of... Yeah, get out of here.
Get out of here.
We'll see you.
All right.
As the group brothers for
another mother get back to the
job at hand, prime real estate isn't
the only way to have an advantage.
The name of our group
is the minors.
Dina joy Crowe, Deandre
brackensick, kiona Evans, Felix
Ramsey, and jalen Harris are
all either 15 or 16 years old,
and they feel that gives them
an edge on the competition.
We have an advantage because
young people don't stress as
much as old people do.
We are just... we're young and free-living,
so I think we have the advantage.
I mean, we're gonna be
like this dark horse.
Being so young, they
bring boundless energy.
[Laughs]
They bring new dance moves.
♪ Ahh ♪
They bring their moms.
[Lighthearted music]
♪
Make sure that you know
you have the timing.
You guys scoot over.
Scoot over.
I'm glad that they
are here, actually.
And that's our advantage.
Like, not everybody has their mom
giving them what we need or whatever.
The best thing about having
your mom around, you can always
count on an honest opinion.
♪ Eeeh ♪
There's someone off-key.
Try it again.
They didn't ask for too much help.
We're giving help.
They didn't ask for it.
You're not gonna learn how to
do it unless you... So, come on.
They gonna get up there tomorrow
and they're gonna rock it.
Yes, they are.
So America, you better...
♪ get ready ♪
They're crazy.
This is where they got
all the talent from.
♪ Get ready ♪
♪ 'cause here they come ♪
Well, if this is where they
get their talent, the minors
might have a long
night ahead of them.
Oh!
But not everyone has the same
support, including James durbin
and Emma Henry's
group, the deep vs.
I don't want to start, like,
a confrontation, but it just
seems kind of unfair, you know?
There's kids here that are 15
that are choreographing it
themselves, and it just seems
like maybe Idol isn't the
competition for stage moms.
And James' frustration was
only compounded as his group
is singing the same queen song.
♪An barely stand ♪
♪ on my feet ♪
You gotta be your own artist
and not always have someone
telling you what to do.
But the moms aren't
going anywhere.
So the deep vs decide to see if
they have anything to worry about.
♪ Can barely stand ♪
♪ on my feet ♪
♪ take a look at yourself ♪
♪ in the mirror ♪
♪ and cry ♪
Completely different styles.
I think we keep it more, like,
the classic rock thing.
All I know is, either way, our version
is really gonna kick some... ♪ oooow ♪
As more groups are busy
putting together a game plan,
rob bolin, chelsee oaks, and
jacqueline dunford are dealing
with the loss of an
original group member.
Jackie's boyfriend Nick fink didn't
make it past the first round.
We took a blow.
I mean, we were... we were planning
on Nick being here with us.
And I miss him already.
And it's gonna be weird.
Now they hope to find group strength by
forming the trio... three's company.
Yeah!
Whoo!
However, it's been a
heartbreaking trip to Hollywood
for ex-couple rob and chelsee.
Are you friends?
Uh, at this point, not really.
This is the first time they've had
to work together since the breakup.
Right now, uh, we are not
really on speaking terms.
Uh, it kind of just ended.
There's just so much built-up
tension and so many things that
I want to say, and yeah.
It'll take a while.
It'll take a while, so...
But working with his ex is
the least of rob's concerns.
Three's company is starting to
feel more like three's a crowd.
Rob's not a big dancer, and
he's really nervous about that.
But I feel that, um, we can do a
good job, you know, masking that.
We all have a pretty big say and
opinion on what we should do,
and so we all want to put input in
and not let anyone take control.
Can we do it, like, a million times
more and then we'll move on?
No.
Yes.
Koosh!
♪ There's gonna be lots ♪
♪ of people here ♪
I don't know what she told you.
Probably lies.
Jacqueline's calling
the shots now.
Jacqueline is commander in
chief and, uh, when you've got
your ex-girlfriend the commander
in chief... I'm screwed.
Meanwhile, rob bolin isn't the
only contestant feeling pressure.
Earlier, Ashley Sullivan was
feeling excited and hopeful
about joining the
hits on group night.
But it's no surprise the ever-dramatic
Ashley is beginning to fall apart.
She's just tired, you know,
because she had to try out
today, and it was a long day and
now, you know, now we have to
already get started on something else,
and it's kind of overwhelming sometimes.
But it's a lot more
serious than fatigue.
The pressure of the competition
is too much for her to handle,
and she's ready to quit.
At this moment, it is crunch time.
If you feel like you don't want
to do it, and there's nothing
that we can say, we're gonna have
to go and find somebody else.
You just tell us right now.
Are you sure?
Oh!
Okay.
Come here a second.
I'm sorry.
I really am so sorry.
I'm gonna miss you.
Are you sure?
Thanks for being...
Ashley... are you sure?
I'm sure, man, I'm sure.
Um, the cameras and everything,
it's just too much.
It's just too much.
Who do I talk to to go home?
For Ashley, it seems like the night
is over before it even begins.
When we return... I'm so sorry.
Can the hits pull it
together without Ashley?
The show must go on.
It has to.
And as the groups struggle well
into the night... all right.
I'm way out of my element.
Many push beyond their
breaking point.
That is what I need to do.
Yeah.
They don't want me in it anymore, so...
I'm so sorry.
[Sniffles]
Plus, the most amazing talent we've
ever seen brings the fire to the stage.
This is what I joined forces
with American Idol to hear.
Remember this moment, because it's
like the performance of your lives.
[Dramatic music]
[Upbeat techno music]
♪
Welcome back to American Idol.
It's midnight, and the pressure
of group night is already in
full force, especially for Ashley
Sullivan, who just wants out.
What's going on?
Why do you want to go home?
It's just everything's
too much, the cameras.
I just... I really want to go home.
I don't, like, I don't
want to be here anymore.
I just, I want to go home.
I just really want to stay
with people that are, like,
really positive and some... some
other people aren't as positive.
Why don't you find just a
place and sit for a second.
So Ashley leaves her group in
limbo as she takes the show's
advice and thinks it over
with the help of her fiance.
We're just gonna wait and see how she
feels, if maybe she'll change her mind.
Regardless of her decision,
the show must go on.
It has to.
I'm trying to figure out
whether I'm gonna stay or not.
I just don't... this is why
I'm kind of freaking out.
I just need, like, five minutes.
For real, five minutes.
Okay, okay.
I'm so sorry.
And as the hits wait to find out
if their quartet will become
a trio, the guaps are thinking
the number five is one too many.
Earlier, Scotty mccreery joined
the four member group, and while
jacee embraced the idea...
We can do five.
Don't... don't... it will
sound perfectly good.
Clint had some doubts.
I have mixed emotions about this.
I mean, we can do it.
We can do it, but it's just,
like, I guess we're just gonna
have to work it out.
And as rehearsals started in the theater...
♪ so get ready ♪
There, we got that down.
That sounded beautiful.
I'll try to keep my
twang out of the song.
The chemistry appeared to be
working, but not for everyone.
♪ Get ready ♪
Can you project it a little more?
After moving to the convention center,
the group made a shocking decision.
We just had to kick one
of our group members out.
Like, I'm a stickler for, like,
people holding their notes.
I'm so sorry.
Mm-hmm.
I'm... I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
Y'all have fun, okay?
I'm sorry.
It's okay, it's okay.
I want you.
I think, like, adding jacee
might be the wrong thing to do
as far as, like, choreography.
I liked him.
Yeah.
He's a good singer.
He's a good singer, don't get me
wrong, but... I liked him a lot.
[Laughs]
Now, as 1:00 A.M. approaches,
jacee must find another ensemble.
I mean... yeah.
Why?
I don't know.
Just, like, what
are y'all singing?
We were ready to just get
working but, um, they decided
that they don't want me in
it anymore, so I don't know.
[Sniffles]
And the 15-year-old finds
solace in his parents.
Above all, have fun.
Yeah.
I was trying, but
they kicked me out.
It's okay, baby.
You know what?
It just wasn't meant to be.
While jacee searches for a new
home, another group is on
the verge of collapse, as Jordan
dorsey begins to question
the group's song choice.
My group, uh, went with a
song that's extremely fast,
and right now, I have
to back up five people.
But earlier in the evening, when
Jordan's group was forming,
he had high standards.
Just sing a song.
♪ Baby, lock them doors ♪
♪ and turn the light... ♪
No, no.
♪ I see you ♪
♪ driving downtown with a... ♪
No, no, no.
And eventually found
what he was looking for.
♪ Everything I've learned ♪
I love him.
Now, deep into the evening's
rehearsal, Jordan is thinking of
leaving his group, and fellow
New Orleans contestant Lauren
Turner is not happy.
He's gonna put us out
there like that?
I don't care anymore.
I'm moving on with
my... what I have to learn.
I'm moving on with what I have to
learn and what we have to learn.
I'm playing the field.
Definitely playing the field.
But I'm coming to some
kind of conclusion.
It's hard to be in a group when you have
to rely on other people for our dream.
Wanting a final decision,
Lauren confronts Jordan.
That's what I need to know.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
So Jordan leaves his original
group and becomes a member for
the newly-renamed four plus one.
I'm officially in the group now.
Yeah!
[Laughs]
We've got to tell the judges,
well, hey, last minute, you
know, yesterday we lost somebody,
so... Lauren doesn't matter anymore.
Lauren did not matter anyway.
When it come head to head,
we're coming for 'em.
I feel like I made the best
choice I could ever make on
American Idol with
changing groups.
But only time will tell if his
decision was the right one.
It's 2:30 A.M.
and Ashley has finally made a decision.
After talking to my boyfriend, I just
felt like giving up wouldn't be fair to
people who gave me the
opportunity, you know?
She's going to stay.
But the hits have been successfully
rehearsing for hours without her.
After so much drama, will
they want Ashley back?
Okay.
Yay!
Make sure you don't
change your mind.
No, no, no.
So Ashley is back.
All right, let's go.
You scared us.
All right, we're good.
But as one disaster has been
averted, another has been
brewing in the dining room, as
Brett loewenstern's group, sugar
mamas and the baby have yet
to find another group member.
We're breaking apart because
we have to join other groups,
because that's the rules.
You have to have a day two person.
We can't find one, so
we have to do this.
Their problems started
back in the theater.
Day two boy!
Twice, they found someone.
Twice, they were ditched.
Whoo-hoo!
He left us?
And though they continue to
rehearse, they know it's either
find that fifth member or
go their separate ways.
Desperately wanting to keep
their group together, Brett
tries one more time
to find a contestant.
You're try... you want
to be in our group?
What are you guys gonna do?
Mercy.
I don't know that song.
You can learn it.
We need a day two person.
Here, let me take my glasses off.
We're... we could really
use a day two person.
Although jacee is unfamiliar with the
song mercy, his options are limited.
Hi.
She's in our group too.
It's really nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
We're really happy to have you.
Thank you.
No, thank you.
We're good.
Yeah?
Oh, I am very grateful
to God, 'cause I prayed.
I'm like, God, please,
do something.
Help us out.
And then he just popped up.
Thank you so much.
I'm glad.
I'm glad I found a group,
'cause, you know, I'd been lost
if I didn't have a group.
Well, you have one now.
Yep, so... yeah.
Good.
Now I get to work with my new group and
hopefully just get through the night.
So the search is over for
jacee and the sugar mamas.
And as 3:00 A.M. approaches, groups begin
to leave for some much-needed sleep.
Out.
The duo of Tiffany rios and
Jessica yance are finished with
what they feel like has been
a very successful night.
I think we're gonna
do really good.
We're gonna show everybody that, um,
you know... they made a big mistake.
Big, huge.
But rehearsals carry on for
three's company, who are still
unable to work out the kinks.
See?
Uhh... ♪ wasn't enough ♪
It's been a rough evening,
especially for rob.
You've got to learn this song.
You be first, please.
Be first.
'Cause if he's first, you're dead.
Can't get around it.
Just do the song.
This song is so [Bleep] Easy.
It really is so [Bleep] Easy.
If you're tired and you're stressing
out about it, don't stress.
♪ And I tried to tell ♪
♪ maybe not yet ♪
All right.
Hold your... hold your lyrics.
Hold your lyrics.
I'm trying.
I don't dance with people.
I don't perform with people.
I'm a musician and, uh, I'm incredibly
insecure about going out there tomorrow.
I'm gonna be performing in five hours,
about and, uh, I'm not prepared at all.
Frustrated and exhausted, three's
company is one of the last to leave.
And as the sun breaks over
California, the contestants rise
after only a few hours of sleep.
Morning.
This is about as camera-ready
as it's gonna get right now.
One hour of sleep.
Okay.
And feeling pretty good.
The auditions are about to
begin, and all 39 groups are
frantically trying to
perfect their routines.
But with the pressure on, it's
clear that for some, their
journey will end today.
I can't do this.
♪ Ahhh ♪
After the break, fresh, new talent
emerges as the groups take the stage.
You're all going through!
It's a fight to the end.
I don't deserve to go home.
It made it excruciatingly
painful for us.
And some of your favorites
will be going home.
[Dramatic music]
♪
[Upbeat techno music]
[Dramatic music]
♪
It's 8:30 A.M. in Hollywood, and
after a grueling late night
of rehearsals, the contestants are
beyond the point of exhaustion.
The stage appears especially
menacing to the 39 groups as
they wait silently in the theater.
They're presently accounted for,
but are they truly prepared?
Before we find out, the judges have
a few words for the contestants.
Pressure I know nothing about.
I'm addicted to adrenaline and
a whole lot of other things,
including wanting to hear
you sing real good today.
So use your illusion, baby.
Let's have at it.
When you get up there and you
perform, perform and don't get
too caught up in the fact that,
you know, you're in a group and
all that kind of stuff.
Don't let that throw you, okay?
Because at the end, we will
make the cuts individually.
And one last thing,
most importantly.
Don't ever forget the words.
[Applause]
What's up, man?
Come on!
[Cheers and applause]
The judges take their seats,
and the first group of the day
was a trio from our
new Jersey auditions.
Last night, pia toscano, brielle
Von hugel, and alessandra gierco
avoided the drama and instead
worked in perfect harmony.
[Intro to grenade playing]
♪
♪ easy come ♪
♪ easy go ♪
♪ that's just how you live ♪
♪ oh, take, take, take it all ♪
♪ but you never give ♪
♪ to give me all your love ♪
♪ is all I ever asked ♪
♪ 'cause what you ♪
♪ don't understand is ♪
♪ I'd catch a grenade for ya ♪
♪ I'd throw my hand ♪
♪ on a blade for ya ♪
♪ I'd jump in front of a train ♪
♪ for ya ♪
♪ you know I'd do anything ♪
♪ oh, whoa, oh ♪
♪ I would go through ♪
♪ all this pain ♪
♪ take a bullet ♪
♪ straight through my brain ♪
♪ yes, I would die ♪
♪ for you, baby ♪
♪ but you won't do the same ♪
Nice!
♪ Easy come ♪
♪ easy go ♪
♪ that's just how you live ♪
♪ oh, take, take, take it all ♪
♪ but you never give ♪
♪ to give you all my love ♪
♪ is all I ever asked ♪
♪ what you don't understand is ♪
♪ I'd catch a grenade for ya ♪
♪ throw my hand on a blade ♪
♪ for ya ♪
♪ I'd jump in front of a train ♪
♪ you know I'd do anything ♪
♪ for ya ♪
♪ oh ♪
♪ I would go through ♪
♪ all this pain ♪
♪ take a bullet ♪
♪ straight through my brain ♪
♪ yes, I would die ♪
♪ for ya, baby ♪
♪ but you won't do the same ♪
Whoo!
[Cheers and applause]
Thank you all.
Whoo!
Wow.
All right, group, man, I'm
really happy I got this one.
You guys slammed it.
I loved it.
[Cheers and applause]
Well done on the group job.
Very well done.
Nice harmonies, yo.
Wow.
Pia, alessandra, and brielle,
you guys were all amazing.
[Cheering]
So impressed, guess what.
You made it through!
[Upbeat pop music]
♪
These three New York
ladi are a big hit.
All right, so that's
the way you do it.
That's how you get it done.
That's how you do it.
Whoo!
And they've gotten us
off to a perfect start.
But for the next two groups,
four plus one and 440, starting
was anything but perfect.
How'd it go for you last night?
Great, great, great.
Yeah?
And how did you end up
together as a group?
They... them four were all...
we started out together.
And I was the addition.
Late last night, Jordan
dorsey abandoned his original
group, 440, and joined four plus one...
I'm officially in the group now.
Yeah!
A move that angered his
former group members.
But if it come head to head,
we're coming for 'em.
After a few hours of sleep, they
hoped the feud had been put to bed.
But this morning, the rivalry
had only intensified.
My group has perfect harmony.
My group has great choreography.
So I think that we are
gonna go really far.
The group I left, they're
going through hell right now.
Listen, listen, stop, stop, stop.
This is what makes you crazy.
Everybody else is kicking for
it, and you're the only one
that's like, am I
right, am I right?
Mm-mm.
I can't say if my group is better.
Yes, our group is better
than Jordan's group.
Honestly, we don't
have any competition.
The pressure is pushing 440's
Lauren Turner over the edge.
Well, last night, we were the
last group to leave, so we got
the least amount of sleep.
I don't know what I'm
feeling, honestly.
I don't think confident's
one of them.
Now, 440 watches to see if Jordan's
decision was worth all the trouble.
Come on, come on.
♪ Everybody say yeah ♪
♪ yeah, yeah ♪
♪ listen ♪
♪ when I had you to myself ♪
♪ I didn't want you around ♪
♪ those pretty faces ♪
♪ always made you ♪
♪ stand out in the crowd ♪
♪ oh, baby ♪
♪ give me one more chance ♪
♪ to show you ♪
♪ that I love you ♪
♪ won't you please let me ♪
♪ back in your heart ♪
♪ oh, darlin' ♪
♪ I was so blind to let you go ♪
♪ let you go, baby ♪
♪ and now I've seen you ♪
♪ and you anymore ♪
♪ I want you back now ♪
♪ I'll be there ♪
♪ I ♪
♪ I want you back ♪
[Laughs]
[Cheers and applause]
They're so good.
Okay, guys, that was good.
We were really, really
happy with that.
I mean, the choreography.
You guys did some harmonies.
You know, everybody came up.
So, on that note, I'll make it
short and sweet, all of you guys
are going through
to the next round.
[Cheers and applause]
Whoa! Whoa!
Yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
We had each other, and the togetherness
and the choreography was up to par.
I made the right decision by
joining four plus one because it
shows our quality and our
foundation, and I'm so excited
because we're all great singers!
So four plus one gets five yeses.
And now it's 440's turn onstage.
But how will the turmoil of last
night affect their performance?
[Intro to forget you playing]
♪ I see you ♪
♪ driving 'round town ♪
♪ with the girl I love ♪
♪ and I'm like ♪
♪ forget you ♪
♪ except the change ♪
♪ in my pocket ♪
♪ wasn't enough ♪
♪ and I'm like, forget you ♪
♪ and forget her too ♪
♪ hey, yeah, I know ♪
♪ that I had to borrow ♪
♪ beg and cheat ♪
♪ and lie and steal ♪
♪ tryin' to keep you ♪
♪ tryin' to please you ♪
♪ yeah, yeah ♪
♪ it hasn't been cheap ♪
♪ but I pity the fool ♪
♪ that falls in love with you ♪
♪ oh, she's a gold digger ♪
♪ just thought you should know ♪
♪ ooh ♪
♪ I got some news for you ♪
♪ run and tell your girlfriend ♪
[Cheers and applause]
With the bar set so high after the first
two performances, 440's fate is not
an easy call.
Oh, God, this is getting harder and
harder as it goes along, you know that?
[Laughs]
Right?
He came out gangbusters
and so did she, right?
I think they all went off, you
know, bits and pieces at times.
[Dramatic music]
♪
Lauren, come forward.
Adrian, come forward.
Erica, come forward.
And Shane, come forward.
You guys are all through, okay?
Whoo!
After an emotional and
exhausting night of conflict,
it's a sweet victory for 440.
All the hell... all the hell
that we had was so worth it.
I would not rather be with any
other three people... oh.
Than my group.
It was like family,
you know what I mean?
And though all is not forgiven,
it can hopefully be forgotten.
Jordan who?
Michael Jordan?
I don't know if you know him.
Um... jordin sparks, she, uh,
won, like, a few years back.
She inspired us.
Right.
What was the question?
She's really great.
After the break, more spectacular
performances get the judges off their feet.
Whoo!
[Cheers and applause]
But what early judge favorite
will go home defeated?
End of the line, sorry.
[Upbeat techno music]
♪
It's 11:00 A.M. in Hollywood.
Surprisingly, we're off
to a strong start.
That's how you get it done.
That is how you do it.
[Cheers and applause]
Perhaps the ten-year group day
curse has finally been broken.
[Dramatic music]
♪
Oh, my God, you guys, I'm so
scared of this group right now.
Yeah, me too.
Next onto the stage, the
duo known as rebel star.
Last night, Tiffany rios couldn't
find a group willing to accept her.
No.
Are you being serious?
Yeah, I'm being serious.
So she poached Jessica yance
from the sugar mamas.
And though they were forced
to work as a twosome...
Does anyone want to
be in our group?
Show of hands.
Their routine seemed to
fall right into place.
I think we're gonna
do really good.
We're gonna show everybody that, um, you know...
They made a big mistake.
Big, huge.
Now it's her chance to
prove them all wrong.
♪ To the left, to the left ♪
♪ everything you own ♪
♪ in a box to the left ♪
♪ in the closet ♪
♪ that's my stuff, yes ♪
♪ if I bought it ♪
♪ please don't touch ♪
♪ don't touch ♪
♪ you must not know ♪
♪ 'bout me ♪
♪ you must not know 'bout me ♪
♪ I could find another you ♪
♪ in a minute ♪
♪ matter fact ♪
♪ he'll be here in a minute ♪
♪ baby ♪
♪ you must not know ♪
♪ 'bout me ♪
♪ you must not know 'bout me ♪
♪ I can have another you ♪
♪ by tomorrow ♪
♪ so don't you ever ♪
♪ for a second ♪
♪ get to thinkin' ♪
Stop, stop, stop, stop,
stop, stop, stop.
So, um... [laughs]
Groups are usually three,
four, five people.
Talk to us.
What happened with the two of you?
Um, this angel was in a group already,
of five, so me and her were...
there was no way I was gonna
let her be by herself.
You know, she was the last
person there, and I was like,
heck, yeah, girl,
I'll go with you.
Right.
Well, listen, girls,
it was really bad.
Oh, my God.
I-I-I can... I can't believe that.
I'm sure... I'm sure you
can't believe it.
Uh, so, girls, sorry to tell
you it's the end of the line.
There's nothing you can do
to, like, try and give us
another day to see what we can do?
No.
Dance-wise and performance-wise?
I sang for you three times before.
Nothing from what you see
in... hey, hey, hey, hey.
Remember what I told you.
Wait a minute.
I don't want to seem
like that on tv.
I just want to know.
It's the end of the line.
Okay, okay.
Okay, that's okay.
Thank you all.
All right, thank you.
Thank you.
[Scattered applause]
So it's the end of the road
for our colorful Jersey girl.
What do you think you could have done
differently to make a better impression?
I wish we could have just maybe
had, you know, a group and
been part of the groups.
So even though opportunity didn't
knock for rebel star... [knocking]
Over at the hotel,
perhaps it will.
While auditions are underway
in the theater, not all the
contestants are on hand.
One of the members of the
ensemble spanglish is missing.
Yes?
Oh.
Hey, guys.
Are you going to group today?
Yeah.
Yeah, your group's on.
My group?
Yeah.
Are you serious?
He's just sleeping, I guess.
I don't know.
We've got to find him, though.
Um, yeah, we've got to find him.
Uh, I'm not sure what happens now.
When Giovanni baretta, George kabriel,
and Karen Rodriguez go looking for their
missing group member...
Well, you probably should get ready.
Yeah.
Real fast.
The judges are left waiting.
Hey, we... are we... could
we have a minute?
Everybody else is gonna
have to earn their way in.
[Lighthearted music]
♪
Luckily, Steven is always
ready to entertain.
[Drumming]
[Cheers and applause]
Dude.
Guys!
You gave us the wrong
cell phone number.
We've been trying to call you.
I did not give you the
wrong cell phone number.
What are you talking about?
[Drumming]
And as spanglish gets their act
together, it's straight to the stage.
[Cheers and applause]
Thanks for letting me do that.
♪ When I see your smile ♪
♪ there's nothing there for me ♪
♪ to change ♪
♪ 'cause you're amazing ♪
♪ just the way you are ♪
♪ her smile, her smile ♪
♪ makes the stars look ♪
♪ like they're not shining ♪
♪ her hair, her hair ♪
♪ falls perfectly ♪
♪ without her trying ♪
♪ she's so beautiful ♪
♪ and I tell her every day ♪
♪ when I see your face ♪
♪ there's not a thing ♪
♪ that I would change ♪
♪ 'cause you're amazing ♪
♪ just the way we are ♪
[Cheers and applause]
So a bumpy morning for spanglish has
translated into an interesting audition.
And after a quick deliberation,
Steven must deliver the verdict
as only Steven can.
Steven?
All right, we're all ready.
We're ready.
[Lighthearted music]
♪
We could use some coffee up here.
Coffee.
Bad.
George, man, you
didn't nail it today.
And you've been one
of my favorites.
Karen, it was good.
It was good.
Giovanni, a little rough
in the beginning.
Congratulations to you three.
Hmm?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Those were the two.
These were the two.
I said it wrong.
Yeah, this one.
You said one.
No, but this... now it's
gonna really cost you.
Shut up.
Giovanni and Karen, step forward.
You're coming through.
Whoo! Whoo!
Sorry, the other
two gotta go home.
Sorry.
Well, that was exhausting.
Edit.
[Laughs]
But now that Steven's warmed up,
maybe he's ready for center stage.
Uh, girls, what do you
need for your routine?
Steven.
Okay, so you need a
rock star and a chair.
Yes.
We need a rock star and a chair.
Last night, this ensemble had even more
tricks up their sleeve...Or their nose.
So we found the noodles.
While the other groups
rehearse, Ohio native Angela
cheslock showed why she's known
back home as "noodle nose."
[Gasps]
Oh!
Oh, my God!
[All screaming and laughing]
Is this what's supposed to happen
on group night on American Idol?
After that, I shudder to think what they
have in mind for our resident rocker.
Steven, could you come up here
and sit in this chair, please?
What's gonna happen?
We're gonna sing to you.
Oh.
Wow.
All right.
A hand for Steven Tyler.
[Applause]
The legend.
Whoo!
I don't know.
I'm not used to this.
[Some kind of wonderful intro]
♪
♪ I don't need ♪
♪ a whole lot of money ♪
♪ a big, fine car ♪
♪ I got everything ♪
♪ that a man could want ♪
♪ I got all ♪
♪ that I could ask for ♪
♪ I don't need to go ♪
♪ around town ♪
♪ I don't need ♪
♪ to stay out at night ♪
♪ I got my sweet ♪
♪ sweet little baby ♪
♪ who knows how ♪
♪ to treat me right ♪
I didn't think Steven could
possibly have any more fun...
♪ My baby, he's all right ♪
Until now.
♪ Well, my baby ♪
♪ he's all right ♪
♪ don't you know ♪
♪ that he is ♪
♪ some kind of wonderful ♪
♪ yes, he is ♪
♪ yes, I am ♪
♪ some kind of wonderful ♪
♪ Steven Tyler ♪
♪ is so wonderful ♪
♪ ooh, whoo-ooh ♪
[Cheers and applause]
Give it up for Mr. Steven Tyler.
Yes, yes, yes!
Thank you.
Yes, yes!
I didn't think you could
have more fun until now.
♪ Yes, I am ♪
[Both laugh]
You want a number?
I do.
That was so good.
That was awesome.
That was good, baby.
Oh, my God.
All right, now you have to judge.
Well, I am partial.
Yeah.
I am partial.
Yes.
Wow.
So Lauren's group lured in Steven,
but was it style over substance?
[Talking quietly]
That was very cute.
It was a very cute, original idea.
Um, and that makes this,
you know, kind of hard.
I hate to say it.
So, um, Lauren's the only one
who's going to be going through.
The rest of you, this
is the end of the line.
Thank you so much.
Congratulations, Lauren.
[Rock music]
♪
Cutthroat.
It was hard.
So while Lauren will be the
only one continuing on, she
still has the support
of her group.
It's okay.
It's really fine.
She did awesome, and we're gonna
be rooting for her the whole
way through, like we are
her number one fans.
Like, it's awesome.
We're so happy that
she made it through.
♪ I was cryin' ♪
♪ when I met you ♪
♪ now I'm tryin' ♪
♪ to forget you ♪
♪ your love is sweet ♪
Bye.
Up next, the best is yet to come.
You guys were the best
harmonized group I have seen.
But not before the mighty fall.
Sorry, you're going home.
As the casualties rise, the
frustration escalates.
That girl gonna hurt somebody.
[Dramatic music]
[Upbeat techno music]
♪
Welcome back to round
two of Hollywood week.
It's 11:45 A.M., and the Nashville
stars are about to take the stage.
They all came through Nashville,
where we first met Colton Dixon
and good old country
boy Matt dillard.
It's been a tough rehearsal as
the stars burned the midnight
oil, hoping to perfect
their routine.
Dissatisfied, they stopped around 2:30 a.
M., but Matt wanted to continue.
Let's see if Matt's group
needed more practice.
♪ When I see her face ♪
♪ you know I'd never ♪
♪ change her face ♪
♪ 'cause you're amazing ♪
♪ just the way you are ♪
♪ when you smile ♪
♪ world stops and stares ♪
♪ for a while ♪
♪ 'cause you're amazing ♪
♪ just the way you are ♪
Thank you.
[Cheers and applause]
Colton, you came out of the box and you
hit it pretty hard and pretty good.
Yeah, yeah.
[Cheers and applause]
Matt, I gotta say, it wasn't
your best performance.
You fell off the melody
and... forgot all the words.
Yeah, the words.
Yeah.
I guess I just, I-I don't know.
Colton, step forward.
[Suspenseful music]
♪
You're in.
Sorry, the rest of
you have to go home.
It's a tough blow to the group, as
Colton Dixon is the only star to shine.
Exhaustion ends up getting the
best of Matt, and he's only left
to wonder what went wrong.
I'm gonna miss all of y'all.
I made it through
all these rounds.
I didn't sleep.
I practiced that song last
night, over and over.
I'm a country boy.
I'm gonna go home and
I'm gonna go to bed.
But Matt wasn't the only
person to have a bad day.
♪ I'll never ever ♪
♪ find a man like you ♪
♪ you got me twistin' ♪
♪ you must not ♪
♪ know about me ♪
♪ I got my heart ♪
♪ in my chest ♪
♪ and done the best ♪
♪ I'm like ♪
♪ forget you ♪
♪ I said, lord ♪
♪ please help me too ♪
♪ I'm saying ♪
♪ why won't you ♪
♪ release me? ♪
♪ yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ you got me ♪
♪ please me ♪
♪ like I'm the only girl ♪
♪ that you ever loved ♪
♪ like I'm the only one ♪
♪ that you want to hug ♪
♪ only girl in the world ♪
And while some of the decisions
judges make are no-brainers...
I am arguing for you to
give me another chance.
I deserve a spot here.
It was really, really bad.
Along comes Paris tassin.
♪ So we forget ♪
♪ about the world ♪
♪ 'cause it's gonna be ♪
♪ me and you tonight ♪
♪ I want to make you ♪
♪ a bad boy ♪
♪ and I'm gonna make you ♪
♪ swallow your pride ♪
Stop, stop.
Oh.
Jennifer's torn.
She connected with Paris, who touched
her heart back in New Orleans.
So disappointing.
And it made it excruciatingly
painful for us up here to see that.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
It's the end of the road for you.
Thank you.
♪ Oh, whoa, oh, whoa, oh ♪
You're quiet right now.
What's going through your head?
She can't believe it.
As more groups hit the stage, other
journeys also came to a close.
I'm sorry.
You're going home.
♪ It's over ♪
♪ I said it's over ♪
We say good-bye to Emily Anne Reed
from San Francisco... ♪ good-bye ♪
♪ good-bye ♪
Along with group mate aly jados from
Milwaukee, Nashville's adrienne beasley.
Don't cry, 'cause you're
gonna make me cry.
Courtney penry and janelle Arthur
from the Austin auditions.
You really lost it in there.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
♪ And you grow ♪
And Aaron Gutierrez from Los
Angeles, who now has to watch
his brother mark
from the sidelines.
You're awesome.
This is just a beginning.
No matter how each person
handles the heartbreaking news,
the end of the road is still
a tough pill to swallow.
♪ It's over ♪
♪ I said it's over ♪
♪ said it's over ♪
♪ it's over ♪
I feel, uh, very, very
disappointed in myself.
It means a lot to everydy here,
but we'll be strong and move on.
[Crying]
As the eliminations sober an
already nervous crowd, waiting
to perform, the hits take the stage,
and Randy offers a word of advice.
Listen, guys, I just want to say,
before we start again, it's
been kind of a rough day.
Very up and down for
us and for you.
Listen, you're in a group.
This is the group part of the
competition, but it's about your
individuality and about you shining
whether you're in the group or not.
'Cause I just believe that you
guys are better than what we're
seeing right now, so come on,
man, don't disappoint us.
It's been a very emotional
week, especially for Ashley.
She quit the competition last
night and she's back in.
What will happen?
♪ Hey ♪
♪ hey ♪
♪ while he was scheming ♪
♪ I was beamin' ♪
♪ in my beemer just beamin' ♪
♪ I can't believe ♪
♪ that I caught my man ♪
♪ cheatin' ♪
♪ so I found a better way ♪
♪ to make him pay for it all ♪
♪ so I went ♪
♪ to neiman Marcus ♪
♪ on a shopping spree ♪
♪ and on the way ♪
♪ I grabbed soley and Mia ♪
♪ and as the cash box rang ♪
♪ I thought everything away ♪
♪ oops ♪
♪ there goes the dreams ♪
♪ we used to say ♪
♪ there goes the time we spent ♪
♪ away ♪
♪ there goes the love I had ♪
♪ but you cheated on me ♪
♪ and that's worth nothing ♪
♪ I'm waiting ♪
♪ and not another day ♪
♪ goes by ♪
♪ hey ♪
♪ just go back ♪
♪ and hit 'em up style ♪
♪ put your hands ♪
♪ on his cash and spend it ♪
♪ to the last dime ♪
♪ for all the hard times ♪
♪ if he mess up ♪
♪ you gotta hit him up ♪
[Cheers and applause]
Ashley shows no fear, but is it enough
to get her through to the next round?
Ashley, it was a little
pitchy here and there, right?
But all in all, I mean, you held
it together and I must say, you
guys were the best harmonized
group I have seen.
You're all going through!
♪ Yes ♪
♪ I want to believe in love ♪
♪ I want to believe ♪
♪ in something ♪
Taking Ashley back in the
group was a huge risk.
Tell it like it is!
That's what the rehearsal part is.
♪ Yes ♪
But in one night, they all found a way
to believe in each other and themselves.
I'm so ecstatic that
I am still here.
It gives me a level of confidence
that I have never had before.
♪ I want to believe again ♪
Coming up, rivals
face off onstage.
They just didn't do any
justice to the song.
And things turn ugly for
two of our favorites.
Did you guys have a member
at one time that's missing?
It's my fault for not
sticking up for him.
[Upbeat techno music]
♪
Welcome back to Hollywood
week on American Idol.
Outside the theater, the
remaining groups are making some
last-minute tweaks
before taking the stage.
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
Okay.
Having survived the night
under the scrutiny of their
mothers, the minors continue
to work on their harmonies.
♪ Ahh ♪
But not without a little
more parental guidance.
You've got to give that look like...
For real?
There's... there's a gap there.
There's a gap there.
So we just... that side is great.
I don't know if this
side... what's this side?
My mom, she keeps butting in.
It all has to deal with the mom.
They get on your nerves, but...
And it seems those outside
the group were even more annoyed.
Last night, members of deep vs
thought the extra help was unfair.
You know, there's... there's some
moms, it seems like they're
kind of directing the
kids on what to do.
Emma's getting frustrated.
I'm getting frustrated.
It just seems like maybe Idol isn't
the competition for stage moms.
Lots of drama already
today on group day.
So get in your order.
That's the first step.
Get your order down?
Got your microphones?
All right.
First to perform their rendition of
queen's classic are the deep vs.
♪ Each morning I get up ♪
♪ I die a little ♪
♪ I can barely ♪
♪ stand on my feet ♪
♪ take a look ♪
♪ in the mirror and cry ♪
♪ lord, what you're doing ♪
♪ to me ♪
♪ I spent all my life ♪
♪ believing you ♪
♪ but I just can't ♪
♪ get no relief ♪
♪ lord ♪
♪ somebody ♪
♪ oh, somebody ♪
♪ can anybody find me ♪
♪ somebody to ♪
♪ love ♪
[Cheers and applause]
He's great.
[High note] ♪ me ♪
As the group anxiously awaits
the results onstage, so do four
very interested mothers who are keeping
a sharp eye on the competition.
So we... we're all agreed, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
It was a strong song, because
you guys have got some strong
voices in the group.
So it was a good song for that.
But the harmonies
were almost painful.
Yeah.
I mean, really, guys, it was like
a bad glee audition or something.
It was... it was not good.
I'm sorry.
There was a couple of you that
stood out and obviously a couple
of you that are going home.
Caleb, you can step forward.
And James, you can step forward.
You're the only two
that are staying.
Congratulations.
Everybody else is going.
I'm sorry.
So it's bad news for Emma Henry, and
Jennifer's prediction for Milwaukee comes
true.
She's gonna get eaten
up in this competition.
And while James and Caleb
will move on, it sounds like
it's a good thing that these
moms weren't the ones judging.
Those harmonies just
weren't on top for us.
Yeah, they had a situation
where they wanted to come and
kind of challenge us last night, but
they really blew it for themselves.
They just didn't do any justice
to the song, and you'll see.
Once you hear our children,
you'll be like, oh, my God.
Those are 15 and 16 year olds?
They've got them
beat by a long shot.
[Cheers and applause]
Come on, rock it,
rock it, rock it.
Whoo!
Come on.
[Intro to somebody to love]
♪
♪ each morning I get up ♪
♪ I die a little ♪
♪ can barely stand ♪
♪ on my feet ♪
♪ take a look at yourself ♪
♪ in the mirror and cry ♪
♪ lord, what you're doi ♪
♪ to me ♪
♪ I've spent all my years ♪
♪ believing you ♪
♪ but I just ♪
♪ can't get no relief ♪
♪ lord ♪
♪ somebody ♪
♪ can anybody find me ♪
♪ somebody to love ♪
♪ love ♪
♪ ooh ♪
Whoo!
Thank you so much.
♪ More, more, more ♪
♪ we are the champions ♪
♪ my friends ♪
Wow!
They just gave the performance
of their life right there.
Just crazy.
Wow, wow.
I gotta tell you, this is what I joined
forces with American Idol to hear.
[Cheers and applause]
That was as good as it gets.
Freddie Mercury's up there,
smiling down at you guys.
I was bathing in those vocals.
Your background harmonies
were delicious.
Ridiculous, man.
Amazing.
You're all through.
[Cheers and applause]
Yeah, yeah!
♪ We are the champions ♪
♪ my friends ♪
♪ and we'll keep on fighting ♪
This day, today, is the
best day of my life.
We will never forget that
moment, standing on that stage.
I will never forget it.
It's like, in our brains, we just saw it
come together the way we rehearsed it.
And when it comes out on tv, I'm gonna
record it and play, record it and play.
[Cheers and applause]
♪ No time for losers ♪
♪ 'cause we are the champions ♪
Oh, my God.
[Cheering]
♪ Of the world ♪
Coming up, it's a battle
to the bitter end.
I don't deserve to go home.
The harmonies were almost painful.
As the drama of group night
continues to unfold.
For that alone, we should
make you all step back one.
Stars will emerge...
Dude, get off the stage!
And fade away.
I've lost everything.
[Upbeat techno music]
♪
We're back.
Hollywood week here.
The judges are taking
a quick break.
They've got a lot of
work still to do today.
It's 4:00 P.M., and outside the
theater, the remaining groups
get in some last minute practice.
But for three's company member
rob bolin, he's just hoping to
get a moment of peace and quiet.
Well, we practiced a whole lot.
Rob is incapacitated, so we're
just... giving him a breather.
We really just got 30 minutes of
sleep and he's, um, delusional.
He's in the fetal position.
Luckily, I always carry a taser
on me, so right before we get
onstage, I'm gonna give him a
good solid tase to the neck.
Just give him a little shocker.
Meanwhile, back in the theater,
the judges are watching
a less than electrifying
performance.
♪ That's just how you live ♪
Oh, a cheater.
♪ Oh, take, take ♪
♪ take it all ♪
♪ but you never give ♪
♪ you give me all your love ♪
♪ it's all I ever ask 'cause ♪
♪ what you don't understand ♪
♪ I can catch a grenade ♪
♪ for ya ♪
♪ yeah, yeah ♪
♪ stop and drop ♪
♪ on the blade for ya ♪
Come on, Corey.
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ stop and drop ♪
♪ a train for ya ♪
Look here, look here.
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ be in pain for ya ♪
♪ yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I will go through ♪
♪ all of this pain ♪
♪ put a bullet ♪
♪ right through my brain ♪
♪ oh, you know I would ♪
♪ die for you, baby ♪
♪ but you won't do the same ♪
[Scattered applause]
Oh, man.
Wow.
If you're gonna cheat,
put it on your arm.
Or don't make it so obvious.
Yeah.
We could see you cheating.
It was one of the day's worst
ones, you guys, and the truth
is is that we should just not
let anybody in the group
through, but we're gonna have to
think about what you guys have
done before, that's
how bad it was.
Corey, step forward.
Holly, step forward.
Congratulations.
Can I ask a question?
Why?
Honestly?
You want to ask the question
why you're staying?
No, not like... I don't know.
Never mind, never mind.
Dude, get off the stage!
Not Corey's best decision there.
Yo, man, y'all gotta talk to him.
Talk to him.
Wow.
This is your boy.
Talk... he's crazy.
Backstage waited two groups
that had made a risky call
themselves, performing
without music.
You're doing it all a
cappella, is that right?
Yes.
Ebony, ivory, and every included naima
adedapo from the Milwaukee show.
The night owls featured Julie
zorilla from our San Francisco
auditions and Casey
Abrams from Austin.
How are you doing, night owls?
Hey, guys, how are you?
You gonna hoot for us?
I'm so excited to
finally be up here.
Oh, yeah.
It was a long wait.
What a cute dress.
Yeah.
I know.
Good stage dress.
[Clears throat]
♪ Get ready now ♪
♪ doo doo ♪
♪ doo doo doo ♪
♪ I never met a girl ♪
♪ who makes me feel the way ♪
♪ like you do ♪
♪ you're all right ♪
♪ yeah ♪
♪ whenever I'm asked ♪
♪ who makes my dream real ♪
♪ I say that you do ♪
♪ you're outta sight ♪
♪ so fee fi foh fum ♪
♪ look out, baby ♪
♪ 'cause here I come ♪
♪ ah ah ah ah ♪
♪ bringin' you a love ♪
♪ that's true ♪
♪ so get ready ♪
♪ and I'm gonna ♪
♪ make you love me too ♪
♪ so get ready ♪
♪ here I come ♪
♪ get ready ♪
♪ 'cause here I come ♪
♪ I'm on my way ♪
♪ get ready ♪
♪ 'cause here I come ♪
On the whole, it was more
than just the band that was
missing from the night owls, and
after an easy deliberation...
Julie, step forward.
And Casey, step forward.
You two guys are through.
The rest of you,
thank you very much.
Thank you.
Only two make the grade.
Maybe the risk would pay
off for the next group.
♪ I never met a man ♪
♪ who makes me feel ♪
♪ the way that you do ♪
♪ you're all right ♪
♪ we never romance ♪
♪ who makes my dreams real? ♪
♪ I say that you do ♪
♪ you're outta sight ♪
♪ hey, girl ♪
♪ so fee fi foh fum ♪
♪ look out, baby ♪
♪ 'cause here I come ♪
♪ I didn't really think ♪
♪ you'd love me too ♪
♪ so get ready ♪
♪ hey ♪
♪ get ready ♪
♪ 'cause here we come ♪
♪ oh, baby ♪
♪ get ready ♪
♪ 'cause here we come ♪
♪ I'm giving you ♪
♪ a love that's true ♪
♪ whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ so get ready ♪
Yeah!
Wow.
[Laughs]
Wow. Good.
That was cute.
Ooh.
[Laughs]
That was very cute.
We've been waiting
all day for this.
Here we are.
It showed style, creativity, the
way you went off the beaten
path with that last bit.
The choreography.
Every little bit of
it was beautiful.
You are all coming through.
[Cheering]
Whoo!
Good news across the board, and
a new starmerges in Jacob lusk.
Wow.
Up next were four
non-blonds and that guy.
That guy was Carson Higgins,
who charmed the judges in L.A.
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
[Jennifer and Randy laugh]
I like this guy.
I think this guy's interesting.
Thanks, man.
With him are new Jersey auditioners Caleb
hawley and Devon rush, New Orleans'
eryn Kelly, as well as
Milwaukee's Chris medina.
Last night, they used the
acoustics of the ladies'
bathroom to sharpen
their harmonies.
When their cue came... okay, everybody
welcome to the stage the four non-blonds
and that guy.
[Applause]
They were all smiles.
[Intro to forget you begins]
♪
♪ I see you drivin' ♪
♪ 'round town ♪
♪ with the girl I love ♪
♪ and I'm like, forget you ♪
♪ ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ I guess the change ♪
♪ in my pocket ♪
♪ wasn't enough ♪
♪ and I'm like, forget you ♪
♪ and forget him too ♪
♪ said if I was richer ♪
♪ I'd still be with her ♪
♪ hey, that's some shh... ♪
♪ ain't that some shh... ♪
♪ I said I'm sorry ♪
♪ I can't afford a Ferrari ♪
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
♪ But that don't mean ♪
♪ I can't get you there ♪
♪ uhh ♪
Hey, hey!
♪ I guess he's an Xbox ♪
♪ and I'm more atari ♪
♪ but the way you play ♪
♪ your game ain't fair ♪
♪ no, it ain't ♪
♪ I pity the fool ♪
♪ I got some news for you ♪
♪ uh-huh ♪
♪ ooh, I really hate you ♪
♪ right now ♪
♪ ooh ♪
[Cheers and applause]
Yeah!
Oh!
Oh, boy.
Let me give you
some critique here.
So Devon, it was... it was kind of
wild and kind of screamy for me,
you know what I mean?
A little out of control.
Uh, Carson, dude, listen,
it was wild, dude.
It was wild, but you were
definitely... definitely entertaining.
The good news is that Carson,
you're going through.
Eryn, you're going through.
Yes!
Chris, you're going through.
And Caleb, you're going through.
Sorry, Dev, it's the
end of the line.
Thank you, guys.
Devon's face said it all.
She couldn't believe it, and she
certainly wasn't going to accept it.
I just want to figure out
some way to get back in here,
because I really don't... based
on that performance, yes.
If they hadn't seen anything
that I had done before, then I
would deserve to go home.
But because they said that
they're basing it on things from
before too, I don't deserve to go.
I don't deserve to go home.
During our, you know, during our
rehearsals, we thought this
was gonna be her shining
song, you know?
I mean, she really killed it.
I just... I want to figure out
some way, if I can... if there's
any... anything that I can do to get
back in there, I'll do anything.
I will do anything.
Unfortunately, it's the end
of the road for Devon.
When we come back, the
time for talk is over.
They, like, straight kicked
him out of the group.
You won't believe the incredible
performances coming your way.
You made it!
And everyone's fighting
for the spotlight.
[Upbeat techno music]
♪
It's 6:00 P.M., and the sun is
setting on the golden state.
As the intensity of group day
continues to escalate, at least
we can count on Steven for
a little comic relief.
And Elaine from Seinfeld is it?
[Laughs]
No, I'm sorry.
High five.
I wish I could give
you a high five.
That was the worst.
♪ So get ready ♪
♪ 'cause here I come ♪
♪ get ready ♪
John Wayne, it's as if you rode your
white horse right into the middle of the
Apollo theater.
[Laughter]
But backstage, nothing can break the
ice for the group that is on next.
For 15-year-old jacee, the past
24 hours have been nothing short
of emotionally taxing.
We just had to kick one
of our new members out.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
After the sting of rejection set in...
There's nothing else you can
do but just keep going.
Jacee found solace in Brett
loewenstern's group.
With such little rehearsal time,
is jacee prepared for this
life-changing moment?
Doing good, but nervous 'cause
I learned this song last
night for the first time, so I'm
trying to remember my words.
Ladies and gentlemen, sugar
mama and the babies.
What up? What up? What up?
[Cheers and applause]
Who's sugar mama?
[Intro to mercy begins]
♪ I love you ♪
♪ ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ but I gotta stay true ♪
♪ you got me beggin' ♪
♪ on my knees ♪
♪ I beg you please ♪
♪ oh, I knew you would, yeah ♪
♪ I don't know what this is ♪
♪ but you got me good ♪
♪ like I knew you would ♪
♪ you got me begging you ♪
♪ for mercy ♪
♪ come on ♪
♪ why won't you release me? ♪
♪ yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ you got me begging you ♪
♪ for mercy ♪
♪ why won't you release me? ♪
♪ yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
Whoo!
♪ I love you ♪
♪ yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ but I gotta stay true ♪
♪ I don't want to go home ♪
♪ yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ but this is really fun ♪
♪ but I'm gonna do this ♪
♪ 'cause I know ♪
♪ that I'm probably going home ♪
Hopefully.
[Laughs]
He did the high note.
An interesting take on mercy, but
will the judges show them any?
She didn't sound that great today,
but she can really stand out.
These two didn't sound...
[Suspenseful music]
♪
[Quiet talking]
All right, so jacee, you
looked a little lost.
Well, I got into the group
late, so... what happened?
What happened?
Did they decide they didn't
want him to be in the group?
Yeah, they, like, straight kicked him
out the group, and I was like, what?
It wasn't a big deal.
They lost their charm.
What?
Well, the group actually...
well, they had already
done stuff together and, um, I
was kind of in, and we hadn't
really started rehearsing yet,
but they decided that they
didn't need me and that it wouldn't work, so...
Hey, man, see, that's what's
up right there.
Yes.
All right, Denise step forward.
Natalie, step forward.
Brett, step forward.
Stevie, step forward.
Jacee, step forward.
Whoo!
Waah!
[Piano music]
♪
Jacee, you've got some
fans out there, dude.
♪
[Cheers and applause]
Okay, so...
We'll be seeing all of you tomorrow.
You made it!
[Cheering]
Despite the struggle,
it was all worth it.
Come on, buddy.
[Crying]
Why are you so
emotional right now?
What'd you feel... what'd you feel
in that moment when you were
starting to tear up?
I was... I've been praying all
day 'cause I knew I probably
wouldn't get the lyrics,
'cause I'd been struggling all
day, and I'd never heard
that song before.
And I struggled last night and I
struggled this morning to get
it, and whenever I heard that
they were putting me through,
I was just so thankful.
[Cheers and applause]
Good feeling, huh?
Yes.
Congratulations, all right?
Enjoy.
Good work, guys.
Even if we go home tomorrow or
the next day, we can say that
we got through group day.
Oh, yeah, we got it, man.
We can say that we got through the
hardest day in American Idol.
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
So jacee moves forward, but
what will be the fate of the
group who turned
their backs on him?
Did you guys have a member
at one time that's missing?
Um, not really missing
but... everything's cool.
We just wanted to make sure
everything, um, flowed correctly
and it seems like he... his vibe
was better with another group.
I'm sorry, who... who...
who are we speaking of?
Uh, jacee.
Oh, jacee, right.
Yeah, jaycee.
Oh!
You see, for that alone, we should
make you all step back one.
Yeah.
I just want to go on the record and say
for me, personally, I apologize for not
sticking up for him, 'cause I
love all of y'all, but jacee's
the best kid in this
whole competition.
You made it.
I did.
[Crying]
All right, guys, we understand.
Appreciate your honesty.
Things happen, okay?
Yeah, right on.
Here we go.
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ ooh, ooh, shh ♪
♪ I never met a girl ♪
♪ that caused me to feel ♪
♪ like you do ♪
♪ it's all right ♪
♪ whenever I'm asked ♪
♪ about if my dream's real ♪
♪ I call, you do ♪
♪ you're outta sight ♪
♪ so fee fi foh fum ♪
♪ look out, baby ♪
♪ here I come ♪
♪ now I'm bringing you ♪
♪ a love that's true ♪
♪ so get ready ♪
♪ I'm gonna try to make you ♪
♪ love me too ♪
♪ so get ready ♪
♪ get ready 'cause here I come ♪
♪ get ready ♪
♪ 'cause here I come ♪
♪ well, everybody ♪
♪ get ready ♪
♪ hey, hey ♪
♪ do you hear me now? ♪
♪eah ♪
♪ 'cause here I come ♪
♪ oh, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ get ready ♪
[Steven clinking his glass]
Steven, this is you.
Hell yeah.
Scotty, step forward, please.
[Clears throat]
Frances, you were also great.
You sang like a bird.
Step forward.
Monique, step forward.
The three of you... plus Clint.
Oh, my God.
Congratulations.
[Cheering]
Didn't I tell you?
You did him first two days ago.
Come on, jun, you know
he was going through.
[Cheering]
It's a big win for the guaps...
But for Scotty, his victory
comes with a price.
This whole dadgum last
24 hours has been crazy.
I mean, with the
whole jacee thing.
I mean, I've never felt this
way before, so I can't really
describe it, but this
is unbelievable.
Thank you.
Coming up, it's been a race against
the clock for three's company.
Hold your lyrics.
I'm trying!
Can they get it together
before facing the judges?
Sorry to say you're going home.
You won't believe what's next.
[Dramatic music]
♪
♪ yeah, yeah ♪
[Upbeat techno music]
♪
Welcome back to American Idol.
As night falls on Hollywood
group round, so far, 38 groups
have taken the stage together,
and from these performances,
another 67 contestants have had
their Hollywood dreams dashed.
It's okay.
Group round has again proved to be the
toughest day for many contestants.
It just didn't go well today.
As most groups are packing it
in for the night, the final
group of the day has been in a
pressure cooker for the last 24 hours.
Ex-couple rob and chelsee were
hoping to create a foursome
with hallmates jacqueline
and Nick, but when Nick was
eliminated from the solo round, it set
the threesome into a power struggle.
Can we do it, like, a million times
more and then we'll move on?
[Groans]
We've been arguing
for a long time.
I don't even know if I'll make it
till tomorrow with these two ladies.
I really don't.
He's just being such a
negative force right now.
Hold your lyrics.
I'm trying!
I just have to worry about
myself, 'cause we're... it's too
late to change groups
or to switch songs.
I'm over it.
They spent most of the night trying
to teach rob the dance moves.
I've never really strived
to be a male dancer.
I may look like an absolute fool.
By the time morning broke,
complete exhaustion had set in.
Look at him, though.
Look at him for yourself.
Nice.
He's completely dead.
As performance time drew near, there was
still a little issue with the lyrics.
Do you know the song?
No.
That's a problem.
Okay.
You gotta learn this song.
I cannot remember this song.
Which song?
See? Low.
Forget you.
You can't remember the title?
I've sang it, I don't know,
probably about a thousand times
today, and I just... I cannot...
you still can't get it.
Ready, ladies and gentleman?
You ready?
Yes.
What's the song called?
Rget you.
Forget you.
Thank you.
Hit it.
Last group of the day.
We'll see what happens.
[Intro to forget you]
♪
It's that song again.
♪ I see you driving ♪
♪ 'round town ♪
♪ with that girl I love ♪
♪ and I'm like ♪
♪ forget you ♪
♪ I guess the change ♪
♪ in my pocket ♪
♪ wasn't enough ♪
♪ I'm like, forget you ♪
♪ and forget her too ♪
♪ see, if I was richer ♪
♪ I'd still be with her ♪
♪ oh, ain't that something ♪
♪ pain in my chest ♪
♪ I wish you the best ♪
♪ but like, forget you ♪
Oh.
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I don't know these words ♪
♪ I'm so tired ♪
♪ but I am really wore out ♪
♪ just thought ♪
♪ you should know ♪
♪ but I'm gonna do my best ♪
♪ I'm gonna do my best ♪
♪ boy, I'm gonna give it 110% ♪
♪ gonna do my best ♪
♪ yeah, yeah ♪
♪
Thank you.
All right.
Let's talk about
this for a second.
Yeah.
All three singers have had a
long journey to this point, and
the disappointing performance is leaving
the judges with a lot to consider.
[Suspenseful music]
♪
[Quiet talking]
All right, rob,
chelsee, jacqueline.
Rob, man, was this your
best performance today?
No.
All of us wanted to do such an
intricate thing, and I think
when we all got our heads in
there, it was just too much.
Rob, step forward.
Sorry to say you're going home.
Two ladies, you're in.
Congratulations.
See you later, rob.
Congratulations, guys.
It was a really long day.
You did really well.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
So rob and chelsee must now
face their final breakup.
♪ Looking back through ♪
♪ the window in the door ♪
♪ that now is closed ♪
Rob and I won't get back
together, but he will always be
one of my very best friends, and
it's gonna take a while to get
over some emotions and things
like that, but he'll always be a
part of my life, so...
We're not getting back together though.
[Laughs]
Yeah, you will.
Good luck.
Three's company, okay?
Yeah.
♪ Fall into the arms ♪
♪ of the unseen ♪
Anyways... I'm done.
[Laughs]
♪ Of all that never was ♪
♪ but should have been ♪
And the party's out.
[Laughs]
♪
And with that, the Hollywood
group round has ended.
Tonight, they put their faith in each other...
You made it through!
But tomorrow, they'll
have to stand alone.
Come on, now.
Wow me, baby, wow me.
As the best solo performances you've
ever seen conquer the stage... ♪ Ahh ♪
Whoo!
With the biggest pool of
talent the show has ever seen.
She woke up the whole place.
The judges must make the
deepest cuts of the season.
This is gonna be grueling.
We've got one slot left.
The final 100 enter the spotlight...
Oh, my God, I'm freaking out.
But only half will survive.
It's not over until it's over.
So join us tomorrow to find out
whose dream will live on...
This is my calling.
And whose star will burn out.
Oh, my God.
I can't say it.
Sync by Behzadt
www.addic7ed.com