SUBTITLING MADE POSSIBLE BY
RLJ ENTERTAINMENT
[Owl hoots]
[Footsteps]
[Grunting]
[Hawk screeches]
MAN: Honestly, sir,
it's such a kick to meet
the famous Hercule Poirot.
uncle Arthur's told me
masses about you, of course.
Have you been working on
a case in Baghdad?
Non.
It's quite interesting actually.
Poirot got a telegram
from an old flame of his
saying she was
in a spot of bother
and coud he meet her
in Baghdad
.
Good-looking woman
Said she was
a Russian countess --
Countess Vera Rossakoff.
Really?
Thank you, Hastings,
for explaining that
to Monsieur Coleman.
We've had a bit of excitement
at Tell Yarimjah, too,
while you've been away,
uncle Arthur.
Well, I've only been away
a day.
Well, this morning,
we had a dead Arab at the site
.
Been strangled apparently
,.
Good Lord!
I say,
that's Sheila Maitland!
Her father's a superintendent
in the Baghdad police.
He must be up at the dig
.
He doesn't approve of Sheila
coming out here alone.
What ho, Sheila?
Will you take that
machine away, Coleman?!
Fancy a race?
It may have escaped your notice
that you're in a car
and I'm on a horse
.
Ha ha!
Always good for a laugh
,
old Sheila
.
Thank you, Hastings.
I say, Poirot,
was that tactless of me,
mentioning the countess?
Could you ever
be tactless, Hastings?
Any news of her yet?
Non.
It's odd though
,,
isn't it?
I mean, she books
into the hotel,
sends you this telegram
,
and then when you arrive
she's gone off on some trip.
Oui.
Hello.
- Eric Leidner
.
- Ah!
You must be Hercule Poirot,
Captain Hastings' famous friend
.
It is an honor to meet
an archaeologist
so distinguished
,
Dr. Leidner.
The honor
is entirely mutual.
Do be careful --
that's Mr. Poirot's luggage.
Good afternoon
,
Superintendent
.
I say.
Ah there you are Dr Leidner
,,..
We've had a bit
of luck with --
I don't think you
know Mr. Poirot.
Mr. Poirot,
this is Superintendent Maitland
of the Baghdad Police
.
?
How do you do
Superintendent
.
Right.
Now, look here,
this fellow who got himself
strangled is on our records
.
Name of Izzat Baqui --
small-time crook,
dealing in stolen goods
,
stealing antiquities,
selling drugs
,
prostitution.
So I want to question
all your Arab workmen.
I still favor the idea
he was buying stolen antiquities
from one of them.
Very well,
whatever you think necessary.
Hmm.
I'm sorry for that.
This is where
you'll be staying.
[Engine starts]
I only hope you'll be happy
in our rather primitive
accommodation
.
No, no, no, not at all,
Dr. Leidner.
I am a man of
the taste most simple.
[Speaks Arabic]
[Sighs]
HASTINGS: Nasty business,
this fellow being killed
.
Yes.
We've had one or two
suspidous characters
hanging around
Tell Yarimjah --
since we started finding
the gold artifacts
.
[Knock on door]
Um...
LEIDNER: You're looking
for me, Annie?
Oh Dr Leidner yes
,.,.
I was just showing our
distinguished guest his room
.
Mr. Poirot, Miss Johnson,
my right hand
,
you might say.
Oh Dr Leidner
,..
I'm delighted to meet you
,
Mademoiselle Johnson
.
?
How do you do
I wonder if you could come
and cast your eye over the beads
I found this morning
.
Sure.
Dinner's at 8:00,
Mr. Poirot.
Where is the mosquito net,
Hastings?
Oh we don't bother
,
with them here.
There's no body of water
for miles,
so we only get the odd mosquito
passing through, as it were.
Couple of little bites
won't do you any harm
.
I'm extremely sensitive
even to a couple
of little bites, Hastings.
[Creaks]
Of course, everyone's getting
frightfully excited
about the stuff
that we're finding here
.
MAN: Ah, Bill,
I was just coming
to look for you.
Father Lavigny,
this is Mr. Hercule Poirot,
he's come to stay with us.
Pleased to meet you
,
Monsieur Poirot.
Mon Père.
I have heard much
about your exploits.
According to the log
,
there was a cylinder seal
found by Mr Mercado yesterday
.
which he gave to you
to bring to the antica.
That's right, yes.
Do you know where it is?
I put it on that shelf there.
Well, it's not there now.
Well --
Everybody on the roof
,
please.
Old Leidner always insists
upon a group photograph
whenever we have
a distinguished visitor
.
If the back row could move
slightly to the --
to the left.
You're not quite symmetrical.
Yeah.
Captain Hastings,
move those querns
if there's not enough room.
Madam Leidner,
what is a quern?
A millstone.
They seem to find more of those
than almost anything else.
.?
LEIDNER: Where's Mr Mercado
Joseph doesn't like
having his photograph taken.
And Mr Carey's not here
..
LEIDNER: He's still
out at the dig.
Now, relax, please.
And look towards the camera
.
Quite still.
[Shutter dicks]
I'm afraid you'll find us
a gloomy crowd tonight
,
Monsieur Poirot.
We're very distressed about
the poor Arab who was killed
.
Oui.
It is a circumstance most
unfortunate Madame Leidner
,.
Was he one of your workmen?
It's hard to say
,
we have so many
casual workers.
Oh God
,.
It's all right, Joseph.
ANNIE: What's wrong,
.?
Mr Mercado
- It's all right.
- Sorry.
I was reading in my
guide book last night
why this bit of Iraq
used to be called Mesopotamia
.
Apparently, it's Greek
for "between two rivers."
I mean, you know
hippopotamuses --
well, "hippo" means river,
and "potamus" means horse
,
river-horse, you see.
No, er...
it's the other way around
,
isn't it?
"Hippo" means horse,
and "potamus" means river;
otherwise, it would be
"between two horses."
So, as "meso" apparently
means "between,"
Mesopotamia means
"between two rivers."
Er...
the two rivers being the Tigris
and um that other one
,,.
The Euphrates.
Yes!
Between two rivers.
[Footsteps]
I should've thought
you would have known by now
that dinner is at 8 00
:,
Mr. Carey.
I'm sorry,
Mrs Leidner
..
I thought that the work
was what was important here.
Not at the expense of
everyone else's convenience.
We finished our soup
,
I'm afraid.
It's quite all right.
I had to finish
plotting those walls.
Yes.
Yes, of course.
It's been lovely weather again
today hasn't it --
,
out of the sun, of course.
LEIDNER: Ah, the fish!
The fish from one of those very
rivers of yours,
eh, Captain Hastings?
HASTINGS: Oh, isn't that
a sturgeon?
ANNIE: They call it a hybiarria
out here.
It's absolutely delicious
.
LAVIGNY: Arabs do not
unclerstand fish
.
That Father Lavigny
is a strange cove, isn't he?
There is certainly something
odd about him
.
Mais c'est curieux, hmm?
He is a philosopher,
an archaeologist,
world renowned,
and from his books
,
I had the impression of a man
of great enthusiasm,
of eloquence and yet he seems
,
not to be able to rub together
even the two words
.
Hastings, perhaps
tomorrow afternoon,
I shall return to
Baghdad with the post car
.
Poirot, look...
I've been married
a few years now,
and I don't mind telling you
I've learned a thing or two
about the fair sex.
Countess Rossakoff
isn't coming back, you know.
That is as may be, Hastings.
But it has less to do
with my decision
than the fact that in Baghdad
,
the rooms there are lit
by electricity
and the sand it is not so
,
prevalent
as to get inside
the uncler-vest.
I do not know how
you've borne it for two weeks.
Well, family, you know.
I told young Bill
I'd make it a decent visit
.
You are a man
of great courage, eh?
Good night Hastings
,.
Good night Poirot
Sleep well.
[Grunts]
[Pot smashes]
[Scraping noise]
[Noise continues]
No!
Nurse! Nurse!
Nurse...
I saw the face again.
And there's someone
in the room next to mine,
I heard scratching on the wall!
It's all right,
don't be afraid
.
Get Eric!
Yes.
- Get him!
- Yes.
[Panting]
[Knock on door]
NURSE: Dr Leidner
.,
Dr Leidner!
.
What is it?!
I saw the face again,
at the window.
And I heard him
,
I heard him scratching
on the wall.
What's the matter?
Mrs Leidner saw a face
.
at her window
,
and someone was moving about
in the antica room.
Right.
Nurse.
It's all right.
Just breathe deeply
.
That's right.
What are you doing
,
Father Lavigny?
I saw a light.
I thought
someone was in here.
I'm just checking to see
nothing's been touched
.
?
CAREY: What do you think
Well, it certainly
looks like wax --
right here,
by the handle
.
CAREY: Mmm I noticed it
,
when I took its photograph.
?
Could it be candle grease
From 6,000 years ago?
I don't think so
.
Wasn't there some disturbance
in here last night?
No candles though
,.
Father Lavigny
had a flashlight
.
?
What was he doing in here
He heard a noise
.
How's his latest
translation?
Don't be unfair to
Father Lavigny Richard
,.
We've only found four tablets
and seals as yet
,
and one of those
has disappeared
.
I apologize, sir.
But everybody says
he's a famous epigraphist,
I just look forward to seeing
his first bit of work.
POIROT: It occurs to me,
Dr Leidner
.,
that your work and the work
that I do have much in common
.
Really?
All I've ever wanted to do
is dig in the earth
,
find out the secrets
that time has buried there
.
Exactement.
The digging into the past
.
The sifting of a mass of dross
for the dues
and the people most important
that you deal with
are those who are dead
.
I bet you don't have
as much paperwork.
Ah.
For the world
,
it is drowning in paper
.
People will be thinking
I'm insane.
Good heavens no
,.
Noises in the night,
faces at the window
.
No, there's something
going on here.
I shouldn't be surprised
if somebody weren't
trying to frighten
the expedition off
.
Do you really think so?
You --
Who's that?
?
What's he doing
- Captain Hastings!
- It's all right.
You see the state I'm in?
[Speaking Arabic]
You know I'm very ashamed
,.
None of the men on the work
can unclerstand me
.
I was trying my Arabic
on that man.
He's a townsman,
and I wanted to see if I got on
any better, but no.
Dr Leidner says
.
my Arabic is too pure.
[Speaking Arabic]
He can go, next one.
- Go.
- Name.
Poor little beggar.
About...
six years old I'd say
,.
Sent into the next world
with nothing but a little pot
and a couple of bead necklaces
.
Perhaps that is all any of us
need Mademoiselle Johnson
,.
I know it's hard to believe
,
Mr. Poirot,
but I can't tell you
what fun we used to have
,
Dr. Leidner,
Richard Carey and I
,,
the first years
we worked out here
.
We were such a happy party.
But...
But what,
?
Mademoiselle Johnson
Oh...
To be frank,
since Dr Leidner
.
got married --
of course, she's a very
charming woman
and I can quite unclerstand
why Dr Leidner fell for her
.,
but if she's so nervous about
coming to out-of-the-way places
that she needs a nurse
to hold her hand,
she should've stayed
in America.
And now the famous detective
.
Oh, no, no, no,
Mademoiselle Johnson
,
you are mistaken.
I assure you that my visit here,
it is purely coincidental
.
Huh.
There she is now.
HASTINGS: I say!
?
Isn't that splendid
And it's almost undamaged
.
Look.
JOSEPH: I find their pottery
crude
compared to the Egyptians
.
Oh no Mr Mercado
,,.,
unsophisticated perhaps --
,
JOSEPH: Oh my God!
MRS. LEIDNER: Sergeant!
Sergeant!
[Grunting]
Are you all right,
Captain Hastings?
Yes, I'm okay.
What was all that about,
.?
Mr Mercado
,?
Well why do you ask me
The man is mad
,
obviously.
He said he was going
to avenge his brother.
What brother?
I do not know any brother
.
What kind of a place
have I come to?
For years I've Iived in fear
,
of being murdered
.
You can't mean it.
I assure you,
Captain Hastings,
that I do
.
But murdered by whom
,
?
Madame Leidner
When I was a girl of 20,
I married a young man
in our State Department --
Frederick Bosner
.
[Bells ringing]
I hardly knew him I suppose
,.
It was one of those foolish
wartime marriages.
We'd only been married
a few days
and he went away
.
I never saw him again.
Frederick was killed in the war
,
but he was killed
in America.
He was shot as a spy.
It was...
terrible...
terrible.
And then about
,
three months later,
an amazing thing happened
.
HASTINGS: "I am waiting for you.
If you ever marry another man,
I will kill you.
Signed Frederick "
.
But this purports to come
from your husband who is dead
.
Exactly.
I thought I was mad
or dreaming
.
Eventually,
I went to my father.
He worked in
the State Department, too.
He admitted the truth --
my husband hadn't
been shot at all,
he'd escaped
.
The State Department
had covered it all up anyway
,
and he was trying to protect me
.
[Men shrieking]
But then Frederick
had been killed
in a train wreck
a few weeks after his escape,
and he saw no reason to burden
me with the knowledge
.
I shouldn't have told you this
,
I just thought you were
someone I could talk to
,
a comparative stranger
just here for a few days.
And you say now that
you have received
more of these letters?
Some years ago when I
got engaged to be married
,
a whole flurry
of letters started
.
I couldn't bear it
I broke off the engagement.
It seemed that every time
I became
even friendly
with another man,
I was warned off
.
And then there was
silence for years.
I met Eric and we got engaged
,.
Nothing.
We married
.
Nothing.
And then three weeks ago
,
I got this.
"I have arrived "
.
But if this isn't
your former husband
,
who is it?
I don't know
.
Frederick had a much younger
brother named William.
He was an unstable child
,
but he adored Frederick
.
Perhaps he feels that any
involvement
I have with another man
is somehow betraying
his brother's memory.
And this William Bosner
,
you think that for this,
he might still be seeking
the vengeance?
[Sighs]
The same night
I received that
...
I saw the face
at that window
.
No!
For the first time.
A dead face
.
HASTINGS: I really don't
unclerstand
why you're leaving,
Poirot.
After all Mrs Leidner
.
told us this morning
,
I mean to say, there's
a damsel in distress
if you like.
We're all in bally
distress this year
.
You wouldn't believe
what a difference there is
.
There's Carey.
Even he was quite cheerful
last year...
believe it or not.
He's worked with Leidner
for years, of course.
So has Annie Johnson.
She blames Mrs Leidner
.,
thinks her presence
spoils everything.
Is that your opinion,
Monsieur Coleman?
No, she's just jealous.
She used to run round
after old Leidner
,
darning his socks and making him
tea in the old days.
I suppose she feels
a bit inhibited
with Mrs Leidner around
..
- Ah.
- Whoops.
- Oof!
- That was a good one!
We don't have to get there
in five minutes, you know.
Oh, that's half the fun
of this run.
You're getting old
,
uncle Arthur.
POIROT: Speaking for myself,
Monsieur Coleman,
I have aged 10 years
since I entered
this automobile.
[Chuckles]
It's none of your
damn business how I behave
.
Of course it's my business.
Now, you listen to me,
Mr. Richard Carey --
ERIC: Oh, there you are, Louise.
I thought Miss Johnson
might be up here.
She's just going out
to the dig.
Oh good
,.
I'll try and catch her
.
,?
How you doing there Richard
I'll give you a hand
.
[Vendor yells]
I'll post those letters now.
Thank you.
Oh, tell me,
Monsieur Coleman,
do you recognize
?
this handwriting
COLEMAN:
It's the lovely Louise's.
?
Madame Leidner
Yes. Why?
Oh, nothing.
It just reminded me
of the handwriting
that I saw recently
of someone else.
Good Lord
.
Why would she write threatening
letters to herself?
Oh I think that would
,
be an assumption
too great to make, Hastings,
on the grounds of the similarity
of the handwritings
.
But if it was so,
it would not be
an occurrence unheard
.
Pretty ruddy silly
,
if you ask me.
Ah, well, if only people
would ask you Hastings
,,
they would refrain
,?
from the ruddy silliness eh
Good night Hastings
,.
Good night Poirot
Monsieur.
The key to my room,
if you please.
Certainly,
Monsieur Poirot.
The Countess Rossakoff,
she is returned
yet to the hotel?
Not yet,
Monsieur Poirot.
Oh. Merci.
Hello Richard
,.
Hello, Sheila.
You're a long way from home.
If Mohammed won't go
to the mountain...
Why do you never
?
come into Baghdad
There's nothing in Baghdad
that interests me particularly.
Really?
- I'm sure we could --
- Sheila.
Don't say another word
.
I am very nearly old enough
to be your father.
I wasn't
saying anything.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
It must be the sun or something,
seems to have gone
to your head.
[Flute playing Arabic music]
[Boy chanting]
Abdullah!
[Chanting]
[Speaks Arabic]
[Woman screams]
Father Lavigny,
do you happen to know
where my nephew is?
I was hoping he could
run me into Baghdad again
.
He's gone already
,
I think.
It's Friday and the workmen
,
are paid today.
He has to collect
the money from the bank.
Oh, blast.
It's a bit dearer
up there now.
Louise has been
complaining lately
there's not enough room
to walk about.
I'm just going to tell her
the good news
.
What time does Bill Coleman
?
usually get back from Baghdad
Oh I do not know
,.
It is variable.
Oh my God!
,
Louise!
Oh, Louise!
She's dead
.
Good God
[Horn honks]
[Donkey brays]
No alcoves,
no wardrobes
,
and no curtains behind
which anyone could hide
.
HASTINGS: No.
The body was on this rug
.
Leidner said he Iifted her head
when he found her
,
but he didn't actually
change her position.
POIROT: It all seems
,?
so straightforward no
Madame Leidner she is lying
,
on the bed half asleep
,.
Someone opens the door
,
she looks up,
rises to her feet and
...
And was struck down
.
Oui.
Blood
.
Very little.
The blood will have escaped
internally into the brain.
?
And the weapon
Was there no sign of that?
No.
Something heavy --
without any corners or edges
.
POIROT: Welded perhaps
,,
by the strong arm of a man.
- Wielded.
- Thank you, Hastings.
It all seems
so straightforward
.
Except for one thing --
if the person who entered
the room was a stranger,
why then did Madame Leidner
not cry out
?
for help immediately
Miss Johnson said she thought
she heard a cry.
She was in the living room,
that's next-door
but one to this.
Perhaps it wasn't a stranger.
POIROT: Yes, Hastings,
she may have been surprised
to see the person,
but she was not afraid
.
I doubt if anyone would
hear a cry anyway.
The window was dosed
.
It was always dosed in
the afternoon
to keep out the flies.
Tell me Superintendent
,,
what is your opinion --
?
is that not blood
It looks like it.
I'll find out
.
Good
It is a puzzle, eh?
The walls,
they are the most solid
.
The windows
,
they are dosed and barred
.
So the only way into this room
is through that door
.
And the only way to that door
is through the courtyard,
and the only way into
the courtyard
is through the archway.
And beyond the archway
,
there are five persons.
And they all tell
the same story --
that no stranger entered
the courtyard today.
And I do not think
that they are lying.
The room of Madame Leidner
,
it is there.
And you were working here
.
So the door to her room
,
it is in your vision
all of the time,
when you look up
from your work?
That's right.
Nobody could have gone
in there.
And you were here
all of the time?
Except when I went up
on the roof for a few minutes
to see Dr Leidner
..
But Abdullah was here then
.
Ah yes yes Abdullah
,,,.
And you saw no other person
enter this courtyard?
After Mrs Leidner had gone
.
into her room, no.
Captain Hastings
came in through the gate.
Wait -- there were
a couple of minutes.
After I had been on the roof
and I came down,
Abdullah was not here
.
He'd crept off to see
his Arab friends
in the guard tent
.
And Abdullah
,,
how long had he been absent
,
do you think?
Not more than
three or four minutes.
[Sobbing]
Come on, Marie.
She feels things too deeply
.
[Sobs]
It's so terrible.
I was so fond of Louise
.
Madame Mercado
,
could you please tell me
what you were doing
?
at the time of her death
I was washing my hair.
It seems so awful,
I was quite happy and busy
.
?
So you did not leave this room
Not until I came out
and heard what had happened
.
It was awful.
?
Did it surprise you
What do you mean
Oh, no, it's just that
she might have
confided to you something
.
No.
No, dear Louise
never told me anything --
anything definite that is
,.
Of course, there were the faces
at windows and so forth
.
MAITLAND: So there's nothing
you can think of
?
that would help us in any way
No.
No, there isn't.
POIROT: Monsieur Mercado
,
could you tell me what
?
you were doing at that time
I?
Um...
You were in your
laboratory, Joseph.
Yes, I was.
My usual tasks.
And at what time
?
did you go there
Um...
MARIE: At 10 minutes to 1:00.
That's right.
Did you come out into
the courtyard at all?
No!
It's horrible.
I-I can't.
It's so horrible.
We mustn't give way,
Joseph.
Well, no way in from
here obviously.
The window was shut anyway
.
Why do you think Mercado
was so upset?
He's a rum cove,
I must say.
It is probably as his
wife says, Hastings,
he is still shaken by
the attack on him
the other day by the workman
.
POIROT: Tell me Dr Leidner
,.,
your love for your wife
was your ruling passion.
That is true,
is it not?
Yes.
Then I must demand from you
the whole truth.
I assure you, Mr. Poirot,
I've kept nothing back.
No, no, no, no.
For example you have not told
,
to me why you invited
to join the expedition
Nurse Leatheran.
ERIC: I've explained that --
my wife's nervousness,
her fears.
POIROT: No, no.
No doctor
,.
Your wife,
she is in danger yes
,.
She is threatened
with death, yes.
And you send not for the police
,
or not even for
a private detective
,
but for a nurse.
I thought...
I...
POIROT: You see doctor
,,
it all rings,
except for that one thing.
Why a nurse?
Well, there is an answer,
in fact, there can only be
one answer --
that you did not truly
believe that your wife,
she was in danger
.
God help me
I didn't
.
Doctor did you suspect
,
that your wife
wrote those letters herself?
I thought that maybe
worrying and brooding
over the past
might have possibly
affected her mind.
I thought that she might have
somehow written those
letters to herself
without being consdous
of having done so.
That is possible, isn't it?
There are, as I see it,
three possibilities.
Three?
Oui.
Solution number one --
and the simplest --
William Bosner,
the young, unstable brother
of the first husband
of Madame Leidner
,
still seeks the vengeance.
First, he threatens her
and then
he carries out his threats.
But if we accept this solution,
then we have the problem
of how he entered and departed
without being observed
.
?
And the second
Solution number two --
that for reasons
of her own,
Madame Leidner writes
to herself those letters
that are most threatening.
I thought that was
the idea you favored
.
But if this was true,
then the letters, they have
nothing to do with the murder
.
But now we come to
solution number three,
and to my mind
,
the most interesting.
I suggest the letters,
they are genuine.
That they are written
by William Bosner,
the young brother-in-law
of Madame Leidner
,
and that actually he is one
of the staff of the expedition
.
Excuse me.
LAVIGNY: I joined the expedition
only about a month ago,
from the order of
the Pères Blancs of Carthage.
POIROT: And before your arrival
here, mon Père,
did you at any time make
the acquaintance
?
with Madame Leidner
No.
I'd never seen the Iady
until I met her here.
The other day
,
Captain Hastings saw you
talk to a man outside
,
and yet previously
,,
this very same man
had been seen trying to peer in
at one of the windows.
HASTINGS: It looked
as if he was
hanging around the place
deliberately
.
That's what I thought.
I asked him what he was doing
and told him to go away.
Bon.
MAITLAND: Father Lavigny
is out of the question --
he's a well known man.
Anyway he only joined
,
the expedition last month
.
I happened to take
the telegram
from Dr. Leidner
asking him to join
into Baghdad
and sent it myself
.
Dr Byrd had been taken ill
.,
had to go back to Boston.
But you do not appreciate
the point of importance,
Superintendent.
If it is William Bosner
who has done this thing
,
where has he been
all these years?
He must have taken
a different name,
he must have built up for
himself a career.
The Countess Rossakoff?
I'm afraid not
,
Monsieur Poirot.
Good night
.
I didn't even know Mrs Leidner
had been married before.
Oh, yes, American.
Went to the bad
during the war.
I just wonder what's going
to happen to the expedition now
.
It's very much Leidner's show --
Sorry to interrupt.
Have either of you seen
Miss Johnson?
She wasn't at dinner
,
she's not in her
room either.
You don't think she's made off
with the family silver,
do you?
No, of course not.
I just...
well, you know,
with a murderer about
...
[Woman crying]
[Loud sobbing]
What's all this?
You mustn't sit here crying,
all by yourself.
Don't Miss Johnson don't
,,.
Take a hold on yourself
.
What's upset you,
Miss Johnson?
It's just...
it's all so awful.
Now, you mustn't start
thinking about it again.
What's happened has happened
and can't be mended.
It's no use fretting, you know.
No.
You're right, nurse.
I'm making a fool
of myself.
It all came over me suddenly
.
Yes.
Yes, I know.
A good night's sleep
is what you need.
Yes.
Thank you, nurse.
You're a nice kind
,,
sensible woman.
It's not often
I make such a fool of myself.
ANNIE: She was never
a nice woman.
Give that to me.
Any sign of the Countess
yet, Poirot?
No, no.
And to tell you the truth
,
Hastings,
I begin to fear
for her safety.
First, there was the telegram
stressing her need of help
most urgently,
then her absence from
the hotel at my arrival,
and now the continuing lack
of any sort of
communication from her.
Yes, I see what you mean.
Bonjour,
Mademoiselle Maitland
.
Bonjour distinguished
,
Belgian 'tec.
You see, Hastings,
people begin to remember
that I am not French.
POIROT: It is good of
you to come,
ma soeur.
It is most interesting
and important this news
of Mademoiselle Johnson
.
Asseyez-vous, s'il vous plaît.
Mademoiselle
.
She must have murdered
Mrs Leidner
..
Well why else would she
,
burn that paper?
The writing was exactly like
the rest of the anonymous
letters.
Yes, yes, Nurse Leatheran,
but order and method, eh?
There is first
a great deal
that you have to tell me.
Now I could not ask you
,
at Tell Yarimjah,
but the good Doctor Leidner
,
he worshipped his wife
.
And he is sure
that everybody else
felt exactly
the same towards her
.
But in my opinion,
that would not be
human nature.
No, no, no.
It is necessary for us
to discuss Madam Leidner with --
?
how do you say
,?
The gloves removed eh
So...
who was there
on the expedition
who did not like
?
Madam Leidner
Oh...
Well, it's only my opinion.
Naturellement.
Well...
in my opinion,
little Mrs Mercado
.
really hated her.
POIROT: Ah.
And, er...
?
Monsieur Mercado
Well, he was a bit soft
on her, if anything.
Mrs Leidner had a nice
.,
kind way of being
interested in people
.
It rather went to Mr Mercado's
head, I fancy.
Mrs Mercado wouldn't have been
.
too pleased about that.
I've seen her look
at Mrs. Leidner
as though she'd like
to kill her.
Oh.
I didn't mean to say
...
I mean, she --
No, no, no.
I unclerstand
.
What about Monsieur Carey?
Well...
he was always
very stiff with her.
And her with him
.
Perhaps he was jealous
like Miss Johnson,
him being an old friend
of her husband's, too.
What ho, Sheila?
Look here --
I've bought two tickets
for the tennis dub dance
.
That's not until the end
of next month.
I know.
I wanted to get in
before anyone else.
Will you come?
Oh, all right.
Yes I'd love to
,.
What is your opinion
of the younger man, Hastings?
William Coleman,
for instance?
I say steady on Poirot
,,,
he's my nephew.
No, he's your nephew
by adoption Hastings
,.
Yes, but all the same.
How old was he
when he was adopted
by your sister
?
and her husband
Oh, er, eight or nine.
His parents died
shortly after the war.
They were some sort of distant
cousins of Harry Coleman.
And where was that
,
Hastings?
In America, actually.
Bill had the most peculiar
American accent when...
I say...
No.
You know well we must consider
every possibility, Hastings.
Good Lord
.
How are you getting on
with our local mystery?
I've learned a great deal
,
mademoiselle,
about our victim.
And very often the victim,
it is the due to the mystery.
That's rather dever of you,
Mr. Poirot.
Merci mademoiselle
,.
It's certainly true
that if ever a woman deserved
to be murdered,
Mrs Leidner was that woman
..
Miss Maitland!
Nurse Leatheran I'm afraid
,,
was quite taken in by her,
as many other people were.
What Sheila's telling you,
Monsieur Poirot,
take it with a pinch of salt.
She and Louise Leidner
didn't exactly hit it off.
We didn't hit it off
because Louise knew
that I saw through her.
In fact I wouldn't
,
have much objected
to putting her
out of the way myself.
Then for the time of death
of Madam Leidner Mademoiselle
,,
I hope you have a good alibi
.
Alibi?
I was playing tennis
at the dub.
You can ask anybody
.
I was always taught
you don't speak ill of the dead
.
Oh that's stupid!
,
The truth's
always the truth.
Louise Leidner
was the sort of woman
who wanted to break things up
just for fun,
for the sense of power.
And she was the kind of woman
who had to get ahold
of every male creature
within reach.
Have you told them
?
about Richard Carey
About Mr. Carey?
Well I've mentioned
,
that they
didn't hit it off very well
.
?
"Didn't hit it off very well"
You idiot!
He's head over heels
in love with her.
[Speaking Arabic]
Tell me, Hastings,
Monsieur Mercado --
is he right-handed
?
or left-handed
Um right-handed I think
,,.
Yes.
[Panting]
Ah, bonjour,
Monsieur Mercado
.
Good morning
Not many people
visit me out here.
You dig too deep monsieur
,,
it is very difficult
on the legs you unclerstand
,.
These people
must have been jolly fit.
JOSEPH: The lower you get,
the more interesting it becomes.
Follow me, gentlemen.
One interesting thing
is that the pottery
found above this level
,
it shows a marked difference
.
Here, I will show you.
If you look at this piece --
Agh!
Something stung me.
A scorpion, perhaps?
Vite!
Merde, voilà.
JOSEPH: I knew
I felt something.
But it is not
a scorpion, though,
or it would
be already swollen
.
But one cannot be
too careful, eh,
?
Monsieur Mercado
[Grunts]
Whoa!
That was neat,
eh, Hastings?
What was that, Poirot?
?
Did you do that
Oui.
I was the stinging insect
and very neatly I did it too
,.
Regarde.
You did not see me eh
,,
Hastings?
But what for?
I wished to observe
his forearm, Hastings.
The left one.
?
Did you not notice anything
Well, yes, I did,
as a matter of fact.
- A lot of marks on the skin.
- Oui.
I suspected but now
,
I had to be sure.
Monsieur Mercado he is addicted
,
to drugs, Hastings.
I see.
?
So where does that Iead us
For the moment, I cannot say.
But facts, Hastings, facts,
those are the cobbles
that make up the road
along which we travel.
Poirot wants to see
if Miss Johnson
could really have heard
Mrs. Leidner call out
when she was murdered
,
you see.
So if you could go
in Mrs Leidner's room
.
and just give a little cry
,
I'll go in the living room
and see if I hear anything
.
All right.
Oh, not a big scream
or anything.
I mean,
not madly terrified
,
just a little cry
as if you stubbed your
toe or something.
Yes, I see.
Bonjour, Monsieur Carey.
Ready when you are
.
No I've done it
,.
Oh.
Well I didn't hear anything
,.
Perhaps you should try it
again a bit louder.
RICHARD: I'm hardly the right
person to help you --
Mrs Leidner and I didn't get
.
on particularly well.
I suppose I was a bit resentful
of her influence over Leidner
.
We were polite to each other,
but not intimate.
Hmm.
Explained most admirably
,
Monsieur Carey.
But there are stories
going about
and one listens to these
stories and perhaps --
What stories?
Oh, the usual sort of story --
about you and Madame Leidner
.
[Scoffs]
What foul minds
people have.
Vraiment.
,?
They're dogs huh
However deep one buries
an unpleasantness,
a dog he will always
,
root it out again.
As for myself I'm always ready
,
to be convinced of the truth
.
You? Ha ha!
I doubt if you'd know the truth
if you heard it.
Hmm.
Try me and see
.
All right.
I hated Louise Leidner
.
That's the truth for you.
That's the truth.
We tried it several times,
getting Iouder and Iouder
.
Even when Nurse Leatheran
screamed quite IoudIy,
you couIdn't hear it
in the Iiving room.
These mud-brick waIIs
are damned thick you know
,.
Good Hastings good
,,.
The onIy way we heard it
was when we tried it
with the window open
.
The window to the room
of Madame Leidner?
Yes.
WeII, that is very
interesting, Hastings...
even iIIuminating.
Madame Mercado,
MademoiseIIe Johnson bonjour
,.
Good day
.
How are you getting on,
Mr. Poirot?
Oh, it marches sIowIy,
this affair mademoiseIIe
,.
But this morning,
I was in Baghdad
with Superintendent MaitIand
.
His daughter is a young Iady
most charming, n'est-ce pas?
?
SheiIa MaitIand
Oh, she's aII right.
Of course, she's the onIy
young creature in the pIace,
so she gets a bit spoiIt
by aII the young men
dancing attendance on her --
not that she doesn't
encourage them.
She was out here
yesterday afternoon
Iooking around
for one or other of them.
HASTINGS: What's that
?
you're doing
This?
Oh we found another
,
cyIinder seaI at Iast
.
You know, this is onIy
the fourth one
we've found on this site --
apart from the one that's
got Iost, of course.
And Père Lavigny he transIates
,
them, n'est-ce pas?
WeII, there's not usuaIIy
much to transIate,
they're more pictoriaI,
aIthough that varies
from age to age.
This one's just got
a short inscription --
just by the picture.
It's probabIy the name
of the owner.
?
How oId is it
Oh, about 5,000 years.
Oh!
POIROT:
Oh, it is of great beauty.
I'm just doing the moId
in the PIasticine
and then we make a pIaster cast
,
and he works from that
.
POIROT: That's most ingenious.
HASTINGS: Have you got
a Iot of PIasticine?
I couId do with a bit
.
Hastings, you're of
too great an age
to pIay with PIasticine.
[ChuckIes]
There's a hoIe
in the door of my room
,
and the mosquitoes just seem to
stream through it at night.
Oh, heIp yourseIf,
there's some in
the stationery cupboard
.
Oh.
I think it's where
there used to be a Iock
.
They've taken the Iock away
and Ieft the --
I say!
What's this?
Poirot?
It's some sort of mask.
ANNIE: How extraordinary
.
?
How did that get in there
MARIE: Joseph!
Joseph!
- Where's Joseph?
- Joseph?
He got up before I was awake,
and I can't
find him anywhere
.
I'm sorry,
I haven't seen him.
?
He's not out at the dig
No.
It wiII just be for
the one night.
Very good sir
.
Thank you.
[TeIephone rings]
[Ring]
Monsieur I wouId Iike
,
to send these teIegrams
.
This to Tunisia,
and these three to
the United States of America
.
[Gunshot]
[Gasps]
Keep them back.
POIROT: Excusez-moi!
Excusez-moi s'il vous plaît.
"Now that this fouI drug
has Ied me
...
to murder
I can no Ionger
Iive with myseIf.
Marie wouId be better off
without me."
Ah, Captain Hastings!
Is there any news
of the man who was
hanging around outside --
the man I spoke to?
I don't think so
.
I've been wondering since
whether the man
couId have been an Iraqi dressed
up to Iook Iike a European.
Seems dear to me
he had some overwheIming
interest in Mrs Leidner
..
Your friend Monsieur Poirot
?
is coming out to visit us today
No he's a bit busy today
,,
sending teIegrams
.
TeIegrams...
Where to?
AII over the worId he said
,
but that was probabIy a bit
of foreign exaggeration.
LAVIGNY: I think perhaps
he aIso exaggerated
the Iength of time
it wouId take him
,
Captain Hastings.
Good Lord
.
Poirot!
I didn't think
you were coming
out here today
.
Monsieur Mercado has
committed suicide Hastings
,.
Not a word
.
Bonjour, Père Lavigny.
Bonjour, Monsieur Poirot.
Father Lavigny was asking me
about that feIIow
I saw peering in
through the window
.
Ah.
MademoiseIIe
.
HeIIo AbduIIah
,.
Nurse?
You'd better come with me
.
So in answer to your question,
mon Père, non.
The man is probabIy
of no significance anyway.
Ah, the so beautifuI cup!
Mmm.
Oh, so beautifuI.
And so ancient Hastings
,.
No wax on it today either
.
- Wax?
- Yes.
Richard Carey
was quite upset.
There were IittIe bits of wax
around the handIe
.
Ah, yes.
CandIe grease no doubt
,.
MARIE: Oh, no! No!
[Sobbing]
Do you need me
to go with you?
It's aII right.
Does that mean Mercado
?
kiIIed the Arab
Oui.
For the Arab was weII known
to the poIice, Hastings,
as a deaIer in drugs
.
[Engine starts]
Do you think he kiIIed
Mrs Leidner too
.,?
POIROT: She may have known
of the addiction
of Monsieur Mercado
.
And perhaps it wouId have
suited the temperament
of Madame Leidner
to feeI that she knew a secret
which she couId reveaI
at any minute,
with the effects
most disastrous eh
,?
So for Monsieur Mercado
,,
certainement--
he wouId have
had a motive
.
[Panting]
Is something the matter,
MademoiseIIe Johnson?
N-no...
Is it to do with
?
Monsieur Mercado
You must teII me,
mademoiseIIe.
I've...
I've just seen something.
And what is it that
you have seen?
It is important that you
teII me mademoiseIIe
,.
I've seen how someone
couId come in from outside
,
and on one wouId ever guess
.
HASTINGS: How?
You must expIain to us,
mademoiseIIe
.
I've got to
think it out first.
Is she aII right?
Hastings...
I think I shaII
rest here for the night.
Good man!
Why run after her?
Show your independence!
As an oId married man
,,
I don't mind teIIing you
,
Poirot --
Hastings, is it not true
that your wife requested
?
that you shouId Ieave
WeII, that's true, but --
And that she requested
that you shouId Ieave
not onIy your home,
but the continent
?
in which it is situated
Yes but just for a hoIiday
,.
She feIt she needed
a bit of a break.
Mmm.
Then perhaps you wiII kindIy
not presume to Iecture me
as an expert
on the psychoIogy of women.
I wouId never have
thought it of Joe Mercado
.
I never suspected a thing
Eh bien Dr Leidner
,.,
an addict is aIways adept
to the extreme
in conceaIing his addiction
.
So where does this put your
investigation now, Mr. Poirot?
I do not know that
it adds to it
,
nor that it takes away from it,
Monsieur CoIeman.
But this investigation,
it marches more sIowIy
than I have expected --
but it marches.
OnIy I hope that it hoIds
for us no more surprises.
Amen to that.
[Knock on door]
Entrez.
I brought you a pair
of pajamas, Poirot,
and a razor
.
Oh that is so good
,
of you, mon ami.
Thank you very much.
Are you sure you're going to be
aII right in here, Poirot?
Yes, of course I shaII be
aII right, Hastings.
I wouIdn't want
to sIeep in here,
I don't mind teIIing you
.
Hastings what is done is done
,.
The room,
it is entireIy neutraI.
There are no resonances
that are ghostIy
of the death of Madame Leidner
.
And perhaps there is something
,,
that I may Iearn.
Yes.
AII the same...
Good night Hastings
,.
What?
Oh -- ah, weII, er,
good night Poirot
,.
Miss Johnson.
[Mosquito buzzing]
[Buzzing continues]
[Buzzing stops]
[Buzzing inside gIass]
[Grunts]
[Buzzing IoudIy]
[Buzzing inside gIass]
[Buzzing resumes]
[Buzzing]
[Loud buzzing]
Oh!
[Woman screams]
[Screams]
[Choking]
MademoiseIIe!
MademoiseIIe Johnson!
[Choking]
?
MademoiseIIe Johnson
Let me.
[GurgIing]
Agh!
She's drunk
something corrosive!
[Whimpering]
It's aII right, Miss Johnson,
we'II soon have you better.
[Miss Johnson whimpering]
HydrochIoric acid
.
?
What's happened!
Get my bag from
beside my bed,
and send someone to Baghdad
for a doctor!
What MademoiseIIe What
,??
[GurgIes]
What is it mademoiseIIe
,?
PIease, try to teII me.
[Whimpering]
What is that,
?
mademoiseIIe
W-window
.
?
- Wind
- Window!
[Honks horn]
That BeIgian detective
poking his nose in --
much good may it do him
.
We can be across
the border by dawn
.
Who can have done this fouI
thing, Mr. Poirot?
Captain Hastings,
how is Miss Johnson?
She's dead
.
Oh God
,.
If somebody substituted
hydrochIoric acid
for the water that she pIaced
habituaIIy beside her bed,
haIf awake she wouId have
,
swaIIowed sufficient of it
before she reaIized
.
Oh God!
,
Poor Annie.
Nothing to show whether
she took it
from the Iaboratory herseIf,
or not.
There is someone missing, sir.
Missing?
The French priest.
Know anything about this?
I was at the post office,
and a teIegram came for you
.
Merci mademoiseIIe
,.
What are you doing
out here, SheiIa?
Oh Daddy!
,
It's in French.
POIROT: It teIIs me that
Père Lavigny
has not Ieft his
monastery in Carthage
for the Iast six months.
I don't understand
.
Dr Leidner
.,
I regret to have
to inform you
the the cup of goId
in the antica room
and the ornaments made
of hair of goId
and severaI other artifacts,
are eIectrotypes most dever.
Forgeries?
That's impossibIe.
Did you Père Lavigny
?
by sight before he arrived
Not by sight, no --
Good God!
POIROT: But on the iIIness
most sudden of Dr. Byrd,
you sent a teIegram
to Carthage did you not
,,
asking Père Lavigny
to repIace him?
And to intercept a teIegram
,
what couId be easier?
Superintendent MaitIand
,
I conjecture
that it wouId be wise
to aIert the border posts
to watch out for him
traveIIing with another.
Got that,
Sergeant Zibari?
Get on the radio
to Baghdad!
Yes, sir.
Why did they have
to kiII Miss Johnson?
What had she got to
do with them?
Nothing at aII,
Superintendent
.
She was trying to say something
before she died,
wasn't she, Mr. Poirot?
Oui.
I thought she was trying
to say the word "window "
.
?
Was the window open
Yes.
She aIways kept it open.
I wondered if someone
had changed
the drinking water that way
.
Nurse Leatheran,
if she had observed
the mysterious hand
enter in through the window
and exchange the jug
,
scarceIy wouId she have
swaIIowed the contents
of the gIass
without the hesitation
considerabIe
.
Then why was she taIking
about the window?
Are we sure that's what she --
ZIBARI: Superintendent MaitIand
,
sir!
MAITLAND: Open it.
Look.
If that isn't bIood
,
I don't know what it is
.
I bIame myseIf,
Hastings.
I shouId have made her teII us
.
What when she said
,
she reaIized
how someone couId get
in from outside
without anyone knowing?
Oui.
La pauvre femme.
But how couId you
?
have made her teII us
[Speaks French]
?
But what did she see
WeII she said she wanted
,
to think it out.
Yes, and that is what signed
her death warrant Hastings
,.
If onIy she had toId us
.
[Whimpering]
What is it,
?
mademoiseIIe
The window!
Oh, Hastings,
what a fooI
that I have been --
when the truth,
it is so dear,
so simpIe.
I have said severaI times
in the course of this
investigation
that this case revoIved around
the personaIity
of Madame Leidner
.
Now, it became
quite dear to me
that Madame Leidner was a woman
endowed by nature
,
not onIy with beauty,
but with a kind of magic
that was caIamitous,
that can sometimes
accompany beauty.
And such women can often
bring disaster --
sometimes on others
and sometimes
on themseIves.
Madame Leidner was very young
when she first married
a Monsieur Frederick Bosner
,
but she was widowed
most tragicaIIy
very soon after the wedding
.
It was at this time that she
began to receive Ietters
that were anonymous
and most threatening
,
but which she suspected
as coming from WiIIiam Bosner,
the young brother
of her Iate husband
.
Over the years,
every time she becomes
invoIved romanticaIIy
with a man,
a Ietter most threatening
and anonymous,
it wouId arrive
and the affair
...
it comes to nothing.
But then there appears
on the scene...
Dr Leidner hmm
.,.
And no such Ietter arrives
.
They faII in Iove,
they become engaged
,
and stiII no Ietter
.
SuddenIy nothing stands
,
in the way of Madame Bosner
becoming Madame Leidner
.
Why?
And why then did
such a Ietter arrive
after the wedding
with Dr. Leidner
?
when she arrived here
This is history, Poirot.
Oui, d'accord, mon ami,
but history of
the importance extreme.
But now Superintendent
,,
I wiII come to the present
and a consideration most
particuIar
of the entourage
of Madame Leidner
.
On the face of it,
any one of them may have
committed a murder
.
Look here, that's absoIute rot.
No, no, no,
Monsieur CoIeman,
it is not the rot.
Alors, the first person to
consider was Père Lavigny
...
who now of course has fIed
,,,
but reveaIed himseIf to be
a thief and a forger
of the antiquities
archaeoIogicaI, hmm,
but not I think a murderer
,,.
AIso there are
three persons
who have the aIibis
that are watertight --
Dr Leidner
.,
who never Ieft the roof;
Monsieur Richard Carey
,
who was working at the dig;
and Monsieur CoIeman
,
who was in Baghdad
.
But even these aIibis,
mes amis are not as good
,
as they seem, hmm?
Non, oh, except that
of Dr. Leidner.
There is no doubt
that Dr Leidner
.
was on the roof
aII of the time
and onIy descended
Iong after the murder
,
it had happened
.
But now it is necessary
for us to pause for a moment...
to consider
...
MademoiseIIe MaitIand
.
Now MademoiseIIe MaitIand
,
was very open with me
concerning
her feeIings for Madame Leidner
.
We didn't hit it off
because Louise knew
that I saw through her.
In fact I wouIdn't
,
have much objected
to putting her
out of the way myseIf.
Then for the time of death
of Madame Leidner
,
MademoiseIIe I hope you
have a good aIibi.
AIibi? I was pIaying tennis
at the dub.
You can ask anybody
.
POIROT: But was that true?
Of course, she's the onIy young
creature in the pIace,
so she gets spoiIt
by aII the young men
dancing attendance on her --
not that she doesn't
encourage them.
She was out here yesterday
afternoon
Iooking around
for one or other of them.
POIROT: I heard something
very different
in a conversation most casuaI
that I had with
MademoiseIIe Johnson
.
AII right,
I rode out to
the dig after Iunch
.
Then why did you not say so,
,?
MademoiseIIe when I asked you
I couIdn't
.
Daddy doesn't Iike me
coming out here by myseIf.
But it's so boring in Baghdad
.
You don't know what it's Iike
But you do admit that you
did not Iike Madame Leidner
.
WeII I don't Iike
,
a Iot of peopIe,
but I don't go around
murdering them.
I just rode out here because
I wanted someone to taIk to
.
I wasn't far
from the expedition house
when I saw the expedition car
drawn up in a wadi.
I thought it was rather queer,
and then I saw Mr CoIeman
..
POIROT: Did you speak
with Monsieur CoIeman?
- No.
- Why not?
He was Iooking very
furtive.
It gave me
an unpIeasant feeIing.
I know it Iooks a bit fishy,
but I've got a perfectIy
good expIanation
.
Mr Mercado had given me
a joIIy fine cyIinder seaI
to take back to the antica.
I put it in my jacket pocket,
went for a waIk,
and forgot aII about it
.
The next day,
I discovered it had gone
.
I must have dropped it
when I took my jacket off
as I was waIking aIong
that wadi.
I rushed aII my business
in Baghdad
and spent an hour
searching for it.
POIROT: And so
...
the behavior
of Monsieur WiIIiam CoIeman
on the day of the murder
was indeed certainIy suspidous
.
But I do not think
that Monsieur CoIeman,
as Monsieur CoIeman,
has the temperament
of a murderer.
No.
But there is nothing here
to veto the idea
that his personaIity,
which is most cheery,
might conceaI the hidden one
of Monsieur WiIIiam Bosner.
Why aII of you Iisten
to this chap beats me.
MademoiseIIe MaitIand
,
when you arrived at the dig
?
did you see anyone
None of the expedition
members, no.
There seemed to be no one
there but the Arab foreman.
Shufta Mr. Carey?
Shufta inak. lnak!
You did not even see
Monsieur Carey?
AII right yes I did
,,,
for a few moments --
near the dig
.
- I'm sure we couId --
- SheiIa,
don't say another word
.
I am very nearIy oId enough
to be your father.
And you Monsieur Carey
,,
did you Ieave the dig
after MademoiseIIe MaitIand
,
?
she had departed from you
Did you return towards
the house?
No.
Hmm.
You see according to some
,,
Monsieur Carey
and Madame Leidner
,
they did not Iike one another
.
Now, another person,
MademoiseIIe MaitIand
,
propouncled a theory
that was totaIIy different
to account for their attitude
of la politesse frigide,
and Monsieur Carey himseIf toId
me something different again
.
AII right!
I hated Louise Leidner
.
That's the truth for you!
That's the truth!
POIROT: I beIieve that he did
hate Madame Leidner
.
?
But why did he hate her
He was, to begin with,
devoted to his friend
and empIoyer Dr Leidner
,.,
and quite indifferent
to his wife.
But that did not suit
the temperament
of Madame Leidner no
,.
So she set herseIf out
to trap him.
And then there
occurred something I beIieve
,,
that was totaIIy unforeseen.
She feII in Iove with him,
and he was not abIe
to resist her.
I suspected something
of the sort very earIy on.
And there we have the truth
of the state most terribIe
of nervous tension
that he has been enduring
.
Oh he Ioved
,
Louise Leidner yes
,,
but aIso he hated her
for undermining his IoyaIty
to his friend.
Are you accusing me of murder
,
Monsieur Poirot?
?
You think I'd kiII Louise
You fooI!
Non.
MereIy I am taking you aII
on a journey towards
the truth.
And I have estabIished
one fact --
that every singIe member
of the expedition
couId have committed
the murder --
induding Nurse Leatheran
.
I was a stranger!
I'd onIy been here
a few weeks!
Eh bien, ma soeur,
was not that just what
?
Madame Leidner was afraid of
A stranger from the outside
And as a hospitaI nurse
,,
you couId easiIy have
kiIIed Madame Leidner
and MademoiseIIe Johnson
.
- But...
- But I do not think that
you are WiIIiam Bosner.
Non.
Of course,
there are many men
who can impersonate
women most successfuIIy,
but, no, it is my beIief that
Nurse Leatheran is exactIy
what she says she is --
a hospitaI nurse
of the most competent.
Oh, thank you
for nothing.
AII aIong,
it had been in
the back of my mind
that one of the members
of the expedition
might have some knowIedge
that they had kept back,
knowIedge that wouId
incriminate the murderer
.
If so, this person
wouId be in danger
.
And in this I was proved
,,
correct most tragicaIIy
by the death of
MademoiseIIe Johnson
.
POIROT: Two nights ago,
when Nurse Leatheran discovered
MademoiseIIe Johnson in tears
...
Give that to me!
POIROT: The scrap of paper that
was discovered
by Nurse Leatheran
was burned by
MademoiseIIe Johnson
.
It is my beIief...
that before Nurse Leatheran
entered the room
,
MademoiseIIe Johnson
had been tidying up some papers
.
She must have come across
a draft that was unfinished
of one of those Ietters
that were anonymous.
And the handwriting
,
it is constructed
most carefuIIy
to resembIe that
of Madame Leidner
,
and the kiIIer has been
careIess to Ieave it.
But now the identity
of this kiIIer
is known to
MademoiseIIe Johnson
.
She cannot understand it
,
it upsets her badIy
.
Then on the evening
of her death,
Captain Hastings and myseIf
discovered MademoiseIIe Johnson
on the roof
in a state of horror
most increduIous.
I've seen how someone
couId come in from outside
and no one wouId ever guess
.
POIROT: I reaIized
that MademoiseIIe Johnson
deIiberateIy Iooked
in the opposite direction
and in order to throw
us off the scent
said the very first thing
that came into her mind
.
But the murderer had been
observing her doseIy,
and reaIizes that
she knows the truth...
so now she has to die
.
[Whimpering]
And that night she does so
,,
but not before
she tried to heIp me
.
Try to teII me!
The wind
...
- Window.
- Window!
However the onIy words
,
she couId manage to articuIate
were "the window
,
the window "
.
MademoiseIIe Johnson
was trying to teII me
what she had reaIized
on the roof that day
,
how the murder of
Madame Leidner,
it had been committed
.
Eh bien, first of aII
you must aII reaIize
one thing --
that the window to the room
of Madame Leidner
was on the side facing
away from the courtyard
.
So...
Madame Leidner is Iying
on her bed, haIf asIeep.
The mask which has been used
aIready to frighten her
in the nighttime
begins to tap on the window
.
But now she recognizes it
for what it is --
a thing of pIaster and ink
hanging on a string.
She is not frightened
,
no.
She opens the window
and turns her face
upwards
to see who is pIaying
on her the trick.
[Screams]
Before the quern of stone
smashes down on her head
does Madame Leidner see
,
I wonder the face
?
of her murderer
[Louise screams]
POIROT: Her scream,
it is heard
by MademoiseIIe Johnson
,
who is reading
in the Iiving room,
but heard onIy because
at this moment
the window to the room
of Madame Leidner is open
,
as was proved by the experiment
most successfuI
of Captain Hastings.
The deed accompIished
,
the murderer puIIs up again
the quern by the rope
that he's attached to it
.
Have I not said aII aIong
that this was
a crime passionnel?
Alors, Monsieur
Frederick Bosner
,
the first husband of
Louise Leidner,
Ioved her with
a passion
that onIy a woman
of her kind couId evoke
.
But I had dismissed
aIready from my mind
that Monsieur Frederick Bosner
couId be a suspect
in this case because Monsieur
Frederick Bosner he was dead
,.
Had been dead
for nearIy 20 years.
?
Or had he
Oh, certainIy he
is sentenced to death
.
But he escapes.
[Screaming]
POIROT: But then there is
the raiIway accident.
,,?
No now sureIy he is dead eh
[Man waiIing]
POIROT: But suppose he was
?
stiII not dead
Suppose he manages
to emerge from the wreck
with a new identity
.
The identity of a young man
who was so disfigured
in this raiIway accident
that he is buried
as Monsieur Frederick Bosner
,
and Monsieur Frederick Bosner
wiII be forgotten, n'est-ce pas?
MAN: Take my hand!
POIROT: He wiII be free
to buiId a new Iife
...
using a new name.
So...
is Monsieur Frederick Bosner
?
here amongst us today
This Frederick Bosner
is a man of abiIity, eh?
He finds himseIf a profession
that is congeniaI to him.
He aIso keeps himseIf informed
of the movements of his wife.
She shaII beIong to
no other man.
And whenever he judges it
necessary,
he dispatches a Ietter
.
And he copies most carefuIIy
some of the pecuIiarities
of her handwriting
just in case
Madame Leidner decides
to take to the poIice
his Ietters.
But these Ietters that
are anonymous
and threatening
,
they do not arrive
when she meets,
faIIs in Iove with,
and becomes engaged
to Dr Leidner
..
It is a puzzIe.
And perhaps Madame Leidner
reaIized the answer
to these puzzIements
in the moment
before she died
.
[Screams]
Ah, certainIy, that is what
MademoiseIIe Johnson
had reaIized --
how the murder, it had
been committed from the roof
.
But what MademoiseIIe Johnson
couId not have reaIized
as Madame Leidner had done
...
was that not onIy
was the murderer Dr Leidner
.,
- whom she adored
...
[Screams]
POIROT: But that Dr Leidner
.
was indeed
Monsieur Frederick Bosner
.
He has to wait 15 years
before the ravages of time
to his face
and to the memory
of Madame Leidner
obIiterates the oId
Frederick Bosner
.
They meet and aII goes weII
They marry...
and aII goes weII
.
UntiI into the Iife
of Madame Leidner
there appears
Monsieur Richard Carey
...
and that seaIs her fate
.
[Scraping]
It's a bit
dearer up there now.
Louise has
been compIaining IateIy
there's not enough room
to waIk about.
I'm just going to teII her
the good news
.
POIROT: He hurries
to the window,
doses it and fastens it
,.
He picks up and transports
the body of his wife
to a point between the bed
and the door
.
He then notices a sIight stain
on the rug by the window
so he pIaces this rug
in front of the washstand
and the rug in front
of the washstand by the window
.
If this stain,
it is noticed
,
it wiII be connected
with the washstand
.
There must be no suggestion
that the window
pIayed any part in the murder
.
Oh God
,.
Louise!
Oh, Louise!
A murder most crueI and hideous
,
Dr Leidner
..
And not content with that
...
you tried to incriminate
MademoiseIIe Johnson
who was good and IoyaI to you
,
who was in Iove with you...
by pIanting in her room...
the very quern with which you
had kiIIed your wife
.
I am so tired
I'm sorry about Anne Johnson.
That was bad
...
senseIess.
It wasn't me.
It was fear on my part.
You'd have made a good
archaeoIogist, Mr. Poirot.
You have the gift
of re-creating the past.
I Ioved Louise
,
and I kiIIed her
.
But you shan't have her, Carey!
You betrayed me
.
You betrayed both of us
Oh if you'd known Louise
,...
you'd have understood
.
No.
I think you understand anyway
.
[Engine starts]
What are you doing here
,
Hastings?
I'm enjoying my Iast
few moments in Baghdad
.
And in 43 minutes
,
the Iast train for one week,
it Ieaves for IstanbuI.
WeII, it's 10 minutes
to the station
and the cab's round the corner
with my Iuggage in it.
Have a tisane.
[Speaks Arabic]
HASTINGS: I didn't know you
spoke Arabic, Poirot.
Just a few words
that I have picked up Hastings
,.
One shouId never squander
the opportunity
that traveI affords
.
- A tisane.
- Yes, sir.
Monsieur Poirot!
I have found you!
What is it, Monsieur?
The teIephone, monsieur --
from the Countess Rossakoff.
Merci.
No, no, no, Monsieur!
She has gone!
Gone?
Yes, Monsieur.
The Iine --
the reception
was very very bad
,,
and she was speaking
from Budapest
.
?
Budapest
- She Ieft a message.
- Go on.
She said she had been
caIIed to Shanghai,
and wouId you kindIy settIe
her biII for her?
Her biII?
Yes, Monsieur.
She said she wouId
settIe up
the next time she saw you.
Monsieur.
Do not speak, Hastings!
SUBTITLING MADE POSSIBLE BY
RLJ ENTERTAINMENT