SUBTITLING MADE POSSIBLE BY
RLJ ENTERTAINMENT
MAN:
"And the men of the city
did as Jezebel
had sent unto them
and as it was written
in the letters
she had sent unto them
.
They carried Naboth forth
out of the city,
and stoned him with stones
that he died "
.
[Woman screaming]
"And it came to pass
that Jezebel said to Ahab
,
'Arise, take possession
of the vineyard of Naboth
which he refused
to give to thee for money.
For Naboth
is not alive,
but dead '"
.
Our reading today
was the story of Jezebel,
whose name has come to stand
for the wickedness of women.
The painted Jezebel
of 2 Kings, chapter 9...
A woman who was shallow
and profane
.
It was she who persuaded
her husband, Ahab,
to kill Naboth,
and for this she was punished
.
Was she the girl
?
who found the body
VICAR: And of Jezebel
also spoke the Lord saying:
,
"The dogs shall eat Jezebel
by the wall of Jezreel."
She had sold herself
to work evil
in the sight of the Lord
,
and the punishment was death
.
This is the God
of the Old Testament
.
Wrathful, unforgiving...
We may find this at odds
with our understanding
of Christianity.
But for the Jezebels
of this world
,
death is the price
that must be paid
.
MAN: The body
of Alice Corrigan
was discovered at the site
known as Blackridge Woods
at exactly 10:15 A.M.
by Miss Jane Martindale
,
who was on a cyding holiday
in the area,
and who made a note
of the time.
It was her opinion
that the woman had been dead
only a short while --
a view shared by the police
surgeon who examined the body
where it had been found
at half past 11:00.
We have several witnesses
who have attested
that the dead woman's fiancé
,
Mr Edward Deverill
.,
was on the train from London
,
and this didn't
arrive until 10:20.
This inquest therefore
returns a verdict of murder
by person or persons unknown.
You look very smart,
Mr. Poirot.
You think so, Miss Lemon?
It is true.
But for the grand dinner
of Captain Hastings,
it is necessary to make
the impression, n'est-ce pas?
The opening night of his
new Argentinean restaurant!
It will be a new experience,
this cuisine of the Argentine.
I didn't know the Argentine
had a cuisine
.
Miss Lemon, are you sure you
will not be able to join us?
I'm way behind with
my filing, Mr. Poirot.
I'm sure you'll have
a good time without me
.
Uh...
[dears throat]
Something wrong, Mr. Poirot?
Yes.
,?
What do you think Miss Lemon
This jacket seems to have
shrunk a little, no?
Here and here
.
I hardly think so
Maybe you've put
on a little weight.
I...
No.
No, no, Miss Lemon.
That is not possible.
Remind me if you please to
,,
speak to my deaners tomorrow.
?
You have called for the taxi
It's outside
.
Bon.
So, to...
El Ranchero.
[Tango plays]
Very kind of you to invite me
,
Captain Hastings.
On the contrary,
Chief Inspector,
it's very good of you to come
.
This is a new venture for me,
and to be honest
,
I need all the reassurance
I can get.
You have invested a great deal
of your capital in
this restaurant, Hastings?
A fair amount, yes.
Which is why it means a lot
to me that you're here
on opening night, Poirot.
Having celebrity never hurts.
Ah...
But I believe I'm not
the only celebrated person
here tonight, Hastings.
Oh, indeed, no.
You see that girl there?
That's Arlena Stuart.
Oh, the actress?
Yes.
Stunning, isn't she?
That's just the sort of glamour
a place like this needs
.
And the man who is with her
,
Hastings?
Kenneth Marshall.
He's her husband
.
?
Do you mind if I cut in
Nathan darling!
,
,?
You promised me a dance right
You don't mind do you
Well, as a matter of fact --
Oh, don't be such
a stick-in-the-mud Kenneth
,.
Nathan's about
to go back to America.
I won't be able to see him
for months.
Well if you insist darling
,,.
Order me some champagne
.
Arlena we need to talk
,.
What about?
I want the money.
She is, indeed,
most beautiful, Hastings.
But for a woman
to treat her husband
in such a way and in public --
JAPP:
If looks could kill eh
,?
Your brain never stops working,
does it Poirot
,?
Ah.
[Music stops]
[Applause]
- Well, bon appetit.
- Merci.
Mais c'est delicieux!
My felicitations, Hastings.
This is the most excellent soup.
[Slow music plays]
HASTINGS: Are you familiar
with Argentinean wine,
Chief Inspector?
No, no, I can't say I am,
Captain Hastings.
I wasn't either.
It's an acquired taste
.
But actually I think it travels
rather well, don't you?
It is a little warm,
n'est-ce pas?
JAPP: Oh, I'm all right.
HASTINGS:
Have another glass of wine.
Merci.
Chief Inspector?
Thank you.
Now, I must tell you,
Chief Inspector,
about the case
which is most interesting.
Are you all right, Poirot?
Yes, I...
No, I feel...
Poirot!
Someone, call an ambulance!
Captain Hastings,
Chief Inspector!
Is he all right?
Yes, he's fine.
He's resting now.
Is it serious?
Put it this way, Miss Lemon,
it's not going to be very easy
breaking it to Poirot.
?
Have you spoken to the doctor
Yes, he's just left.
,?
So what did he say
I demand at once
,,
a second opinion!
I think we should wait Poirot
,.
The doctor's taken some tests
,
but it'll be a week
before he's certain.
But I am certain, Hastings.
Hercule Poirot,
he is not obese!
Medically obese Mr Poirot
,.,
it's not quite the same.
HASTINGS:
It may have Ied to a probIem
with your heart, which is what
?
caused the -- you know
WeII we should be gratefuI
,
it's nothing more serious.
MISS LEMON:
You can come home tomorrow.
But it's going
to mean pIenty of rest,
Iight exercise,
and a strict diet
.
[Sighs]
HASTINGS: "Hoping you'II soon
be back on your feet."
Oh?
From everyone at the Forensic
Department ScotIand Yard
,.
Oh, here's one from
the BeIgian Ambassador
.
It seems that the whoIe
of London
knows what has occurred
,
Hastings.
HASTINGS:
Oh, not more maiI, Miss Lemon!
This is from the doctor
.
I teIephoned him this morning
,
and he sent it round.
The Sandy Cove HoteI
,
just off the south coast.
For the Iast coupIe of years,
it's been run
as a heaIth resort.
It's highIy recommended
.
"A strict regime of diet
and exercise,
sunshine and the sea "
.
No, Miss Lemon.
This is not for Poirot.
Your doctor disagrees,
Mr Poirot and so do I
.,.
[Sighs]
MISS LEMON: We might have Iost
you the other night and
,...
WeII it doesn't even bear
,
thinking about it.
Doctor's orders
.
I've booked you a room
for two weeks.
HASTINGS:
Oh don't worry Poirot
,,,
I'm sure you'II enjoy it.
I'm sure you wiII, too,
Captain Hastings.
You're going as weII.
What?
WeII you didn't expect
,
Mr. Poirot to go on his own!
[GuIIs crying]
MAN: Let's see...it's
two pounds and nine pence
.
POIROT: Hastings,
the hoteI it is on an isIand
,.
WeII don't worry Poirot you
,,,
won't have to go on a boat.
There's...that to carry
you over the causeway.
AII aboard pIease!
,
We Ieave in a minute!
- HeIIo.
Are you on board for
?
the isIand of the Iost souIs
Oh, Patrick, I don't think it's
going to be as bad as aII that
.
I'm Patrick Redfern
My wife, Christine.
Madame
.
HercuIe Poirot.
This is my associate,
Captain Hastings.
?
How do you do
PATRICK: HercuIe Poirot?
?
The famous detective
POIROT: Oui.
WeII, that wiII certainIy
Iiven things up.
[Engine sputters]
Here we go.
[Coughs]
CHRISTINE: You're not here
on business, Mr. Poirot?
No I come on the recommendation
,
of my doctor
.
We aII need a rest
from time to time.
Nothing Iike a bit of sun
and sea air
.
I have to be carefuI
of the sun.
I burn up in a minute.
I say, Poirot.
There's ArIena Stuart!
Do you remember?
EI Ranchero?
That was an evening, Hastings,
that I was trying to forget.
??
- Patrick How could you
- What?
That woman, ArIena Stuart!
She's staying here, isn't she?
I had no idea
.
Don't Iie to me!
It was your idea to come here
,
and I wondered why
and now I know.
Christine...
You knew she was going to be
here and you foIIowed her!
No!
You know, sometimes
I don't understand you
.
DarIing...
Sometimes, you can be
so hurtfuI. [Crying]
- Christine!
- Patrick darIing!
,
Was that Christine I just saw?
Yes, she just went in
to get out of the sun.
It's so wonderfuI to see you
.
What a wonderfuI surprise
It's wonderfuI to see you too
,.
Oh, Mr. Poirot.
This is an old friend of mine
,
weII new friend I should say
,,,
ArIena Stuart.
Madame
.
We met at a cocktaiI party.
And it was Iove at first sight
.
How Iong are you staying?
- A week.
- Thank goodness
.
This pIace is nice enough,
but it's a rather stuffy crowd
.
[Laughs]
ArIena?
ARLENA: [Laughs]
You're Iate for tennis.
ActuaIIy, Kenneth,
I'm not pIaying.
Look who's just turned up
.
- Redfern.
- How are you, MarshaII?
You did say you'd pIay.
We've got Rosamund waiting
.
WeII, teII her
I've got a headache
.
Come on, I'm going
to show you around
.
But I haven't
even checked in yet
.
Oh you can do that Iater
,.
This way!
Why do you Iet her treat you
that way?
- LioneI...
- I hate her!
I wish you'd never married her!
WOMAN: Yes?
Uh, HercuIe Poirot.
And Captain Hastings
.
Oh, yes, Mr. Poirot.
WeIcome to the Sandy Cove HoteI
.
I hope you have a very happy
and a very heaIthy stay
.
Merci, madame.
I had a Ietter
from your doctor
,
and you'II be pIeased to know
that I've worked out
a compIete program
for your stay here.
We'II be combining
the naturaI goodness
of the sea and the sunshine
with our indoor swimming pooI
,
gymnasium,
heated oiI therapy
and steam room
,
brisk daiIy exercise
and of course a strict diet
,,.
[BeII dings]
WiIIiam, show Mr. Poirot
and Captain Hastings
to their rooms, pIease.
Yes, Mrs. CastIe.
Lunch wiII be served at 1 00
:.
You have a sea view, sir.
Most of the rooms
have a sea view.
It comes with being
on an isIand.
It is evident yes
,.
If you need anything there's
,
shops on the mainIand.
A Iibrary, post office,
and a decent restaurant
.
And if you get peckish
or anything,
you can aIways ask me
to run over.
Right, sir?
Thank you.
Hastings?
Oh.
Right.
Thank you, sir.
You're next-door
.
Right.
[GuIIs caIIing]
[ArIena Iaughing]
PATRICK: Go for a swim just down
there, Iook.
ARLENA: Oh, yes, there's
a IoveIy spot...
I say what a spIendid view!
,
Yes indeed Hastings
,,,
it is of great interest.
How are you feeIing, Poirot?
Not too tired
after the journey?
Hastings I am recovered
,.
I am not an invaIid
.
There's no need to act
Iike a mother chicken.
Hen.
Thank you, Hastings,
ça va?
AbsoIuteIy.
[dock strikes hour]
Lunch!
HASTINGS: Thank you.
Oh.
It is for the best,
you know, Poirot?
Peut-être, mon ami.
Your heaIth.
Here's to yours.
Waiter!
If you pIease, teII me
what is in my gIass?
NettIe water.
Mrs. CastIe swears by it.
Monsieur Poirot!
Oh MademoiseIIe
,...
DarnIey, is it not?
How nice
that you remember me.
[Laughing]
- We met in...Egypt.
- Egypt.
I was on hoIiday
.
You were soIving a murder
Comme toujours, mademoiselle.
Pardon.
You have not met my associate,
Captain Hastings.
?
How do you do
Captain Hastings,
this is MademoiseIIe DarnIey
,
a dressmaker
of the most renown.
Aw.
WiII you pIease to join us,
MademoiseIIe?
I'd be deIighted
.
Thank you.
Merci.
I see they've got you
on punishment rations.
Uh.
You are here aIso
for the heaIth mademoiseIIe
,?
PartIy.
AIso I decided to catch up
,
with an old friend
Kenneth MarshaII,
Have you met him?
We've seen him.
He and I were what you might
caII "childhood sweethearts."
A Iong, Iong time ago.
Now we're just good friends
.
He suggested I come down.
Do you know his wife?
His first wife Linda
,.
A sweet girI.
She died a few years ago
of typhoid
.
Very sad
I'm afraid I'm not
so dose to ArIena.
Thank you.
The second Madame MarshaII
.
I'm sorry?
Pardon you were speaking
,
of Madame ArIena MarshaII
.
Yes, weII...what can I say?
She treats him dreadfuIIy
.
And she's up to her eyes
in scandaI
.
I mean, that business
with Erskine,
for a start.
But this is a name
I do not know
.
DARNLEY: Sir Roger Erskine.
ElderIy unattached
,,
very, very rich.
He's foIIowing her around town
Iike a puppy and then suddenIy
,,
dropped dead
,
Ieft her his entire fortune.
Oh.
So Madame MarshaII is a woman
,
of weaIth in her own right?
Mm-hmm.
Maybe that's why Kenneth's
married her
.
But I teII you this,
Mr. Poirot.
That woman is troubIe.
You wait and see
.
[Both Iaughing]
Don't spIash me!
[Screams]
MarveIous view,
don't you think?
Yes indeed
,.
Miss Brewster.
EmiIy Brewster.
MademoiseIIe
.
And I know who you are
You're HercuIe Poirot.
POIROT: Oui.
And you must be
Captain Hastings.
That's right.
Word's got around
that you were here.
Now don't teII me
,.
There's been
a gruesome murder somewhere
,
and you think there's
a homicidaI maniac
Iurking among the hoteI guests!
No no mademoiseIIe
,,.
I am here for my heaIth.
How disappointing
.
Of course if you did
,
want to commit a murder
this would be
the perfect pIace.
You beIieve so mademoiseIIe
,?
EMILY:
PeopIe away from home.
Everyone's got
a reason to be here.
But if you secretIy wanted
to get dose to someone
because you wanted
to finish them off,
this is where you'd come
.
But teII me mademoiseIIe
,,
who would be the target
of such an attack
here at the hoteI?
WeII I don't know
,.
ArIena Stuart, perhaps?
I'd happiIy stick
a hat pin in her, or whatever.
But to come upon her
sunbathing on the beach, huh,
it's the best chance
I'd ever get.
But sureIy,
nobody could think of murder
in such a beautifuI pIace?
No, no, no.
No, Hastings.
It is romantic, yes.
It is peacefuI.
The sun shines,
the sea, it is bIue...
But you forget, mon ami,
there is eviI everywhere
under the sun
.
What?
Even here?
VICAR: EspeciaIIy here.
It's interesting what
you're saying, Mr. Poirot.
It's aImost a quotation
from Ecdesiastes.
"Yea, aIso the heart of the son
of man is fuII of eviI,
and madness is at their hearts
whiIe they Iive."
You are of the church,
Monsieur...?
Lane.
Stephen Lane.
I was.
But then I was iII.
My wife...
You see...
WeII, it's a Iong story.
But that's why I'm here.
It's for my heaIth.
Anyway...
you don't have to be
of the church
to recognize eviI, Mr. Poirot.
I see it there.
I recognize it.
It's reaI.
Ah, this must be that
Iadder down to Pixy Cove
.
POIROT: Comment?
HASTINGS: Pixy Cove, it's what
they caII this beach.
For me, Hastings, I caII it
too steep and too dangerous
.
Hastings, you see that boat
?
with the red saiI
HASTINGS:
Yes I noticed it this morning
,.
POIROT: It is a coIor
most strange, n'est-ce pas?
I hadn't reaIIy
thought about it.
I suppose the saiIs
ought to be white.
POIROT: And for me aIso
,
it is a pIace
most strange to have moored
.
MAN: Mr. Poirot?
Monsieur?
My name's Barry.
Major Barry.
Major.
BARRY: I was outside just now
,
and I couldn't
heIp noticing you.
I wondered what
you might be doing down here
at the Sandy Cove HoteI
.
I am here Iike aII the rest.
For my heaIth.
ReaIIy?
WeII, if you'II take a tip
from an old soldier,
I wouldn't have said this isIand
was the heaIthiest pIace to be,
at the moment.
Just a thought.
HASTINGS: How very odd!
I have a great fear, Hastings.
?
What do you mean
WeII, the Major
who gives the warning...
the vicar who speaks of eviI...
the husband who watches
as his wife deceives him
.
The soIving of the murder
is aII too often
the work of Poirot, mon ami.
This time the murder
,...
it is something
which I must try to prevent.
Hmm.
The steam cabinet
is wideIy used
throughout the Americas,
Mr. Poirot.
It purifies the skin,
and it is aIso recommended
as an aid to respiration
and the circuIation
of the bIood.
WeII, for me, it is
a new experience madame
,.
I'm sure you'II enjoy it.
Come, come, come,
there's nothing
to be afraid of
.
,.?
What do you say Mr BIatt
[Sighs]
Come aIong, now.
Horace BIatt.
Forgive me
if I don't shake hands
.
HercuIe Poirot.
The famous sIeuth, eh?
?
You down here on a job
No, no.
BLATT:
It doesn't Iook Iike it
.
[Laughs]
Nice pIace, eh?
Not quite DeauviIIe
or Nice,
of course but it does
,....
[Sighs]
?
You are on hoIiday
I spend quite
a bit of time here.
SaiIing.
The best fun in the world
,
if you ask me.
You've probabIy seen me,
bobbing around
.
Oh, yes.
You have the boat
?
with the red saiI
BLATT: That's me.
I use the hoteI as a base.
It's convenient
for my business.
And what business is that
,
Monsieur BIatt?
Oh...a bit of this,
a bit of that.
[Laughs]
So, you're
HercuIe Poirot, eh?
The strange thing is,
I thought you were dead
.
[Laughing]
DARNLEY:
?
Why don't you divorce her
KENNETH:
You don't understand
.
DARNLEY: You don't Iove her
KENNETH: It's got nothing
to do with it.
I married her
.
DARNLEY: Your own happiness
has got nothing to do it?
KENNETH: It's not a question
of my happiness.
DARNLEY: So you're too proud
,,
is that what it is?
What about LioneI?
KENNETH: What about him?
DARNLEY: Don't you see
how unhappy he is?
KENNETH: Oh, I can
Iook after LioneI.
DARNLEY: I'm sure,
but don't you ever think
that for both your sakes
that you ought to
?
get rid of ArIena
KENNETH:
,?
Do you mean divorce her
DARNLEY: Of course.
KENNETH: ArIena's my wife,
and that's aII there is to it
.
DARNLEY:
"'TiI death us do part "
.
ExactIy.
DARNLEY: I see.
[Door doses]
HASTINGS: Ah.
There you are, Poirot!
What can I get you?
Oh. Hastings, thank you,
that is most kind of you.
A IittIe crême de cassis
.
Crême de cassis
I'm very sorry, sir,
not for you.
POIROT: Comment?
No aIcohoI, sir.
Mrs CastIe's orders
..
Oh bad Iuck Mr Poirot
,,..
There'II be dinner
in a minute.
Not that that's anything
to write home about.
[ChuckIing]
Do come and sit over here
,
Mr. Poirot.
POIROT:
Merci MademoiseIIe Brewster
,.
Merci.
HASTINGS: I was just taIking
about my trip round the isIand
.
I dimbed down to Pixy Cove
?
- Did you find the cave
- Damn!
Oh!
That was siIIy of me.
Uh, what cave?
Oh, I've heard it said that
there's a cave on Pixy Cove.
It's quite hard to find
.
There's just a crack
in the rock at the opening,
and then it widens out
.
And that's where you'II
find the buried treasure!
[Laughs]
There's no such thing
as buried treasure.
That's what you get
in children's books.
Now, now, LioneI.
Whatever you say LioneI dear
,,.
DARNLEY: So...
who's for tennis,
tomorrow morning?
How about you, Mr. Poirot?
No, no, it is most kind
of you mademoiseIIe
,.
But I think that the tennis,
it is not for me.
I'II pIay.
I mean, if there's
not too much sun.
How about you,
Captain Hastings?
Oh, yes.
I brought down my racket
.
And I'II make up a four
,
if it's not too earIy.
I have some typing to do
in the morning.
?
How about 12:00 midday
That's fine.
[BeII rings]
That's dinner!
ARLENA: I'm starving.
It had better
not to be cabbage soup.
Mrs. MarshaII, you have
a teIephone caII.
KENNETH: What?
At this time?
?
Who could that be
Roger or CharIie
or Dominic or MichaeI.
Could be anyone
.
You go on without me.
I need to powder my nose
.
KENNETH:
After you, Miss Brewster.
EMILY: Thank you.
Oh, I'm so hungry.
It must be aII this sea air.
HeIIo?
MAN: Arlena, my dear.
Oh, heIIo.
Yes.
WeII, it's a IittIe bit
difficuIt at the moment
.
Yes, of course.
HeIIo, Mr. Poirot.
Monsieur Redfern
.
?
How was dinner
It was...
how shaII I say?
Not substantiaI.
WeII, that's true.
Merci.
Monsieur Redfern may I ask you
,
?
what you do for your work
I'm a journaIist.
What, for the newspapers?
Yes, for the city pages.
I'm freeIance.
Anything that pays.
So, you're not here,
I think, for your heaIth.
No, I'm here
to enjoy myseIf.
Christine's the one who
has to Iook after herseIf.
Oh, yes.
Madame Redfern
.
You have a wife
most charming, monsieur.
And who, I think,
of you aIso is most fond
.
I'm fond of her
I'm gIad to hear it
.
Mr. Poirot, are you trying
to teII me something?
OnIy this Monsieur Redfern
,.
I wonder why if it is necessary
,
for you to conduct an affair,
here on this isIand
,,
with ArIena Stuart,
you choose to do it before
the very eyes of your wife!
What?
Who've you been taIking to,
Mr. Poirot?
Miss DarnIey?
Or that BibIe-bashing vicar?
Just because a woman
is good-Iooking
,
everyone has to come down
on her Iike a sack of coaIs.
Monsieur Redfern, I try
onIy to prevent occurring events
of which I have great fear.
WeII maybe you should just
...
mind your own damn business
.
[GuIIs caIIing]
[BeII rings]
Oh! LioneI!
Where've you been?
I went to the mainIand
.
To the Iibrary.
So I see.
I was thinking of going
over to GuII Cove
to do some sketching
before tennis.
?
Why don't you come with me
- Um, weII...
- WeII, you can have a swim.
Come on you don't want to be
,
skuIking and reading aII day.
AII right.
I'II meet you here
in an hour from now. 10:30.
[Sighs]
Thank you.
Ah Good morning
..
?
Did you have a good ride
Fine, thank you.
I'm just off myseIf.
I have friends on the mainIand
.
Enjoy your day
?
When do you Ieave again
- A few minutes, sir.
- Good.
What?!
AII right, Poirot?
Thank you, Hastings.
Is that not the boat
of Monsieur BIatt?
HASTINGS: I think so.
POIROT:
It is strange, n'est ce-pas?
Today he has the boat
with a white saiI.
Yes.
So, how are you feeIing, Poirot?
You refer to my heaIth,
Hastings?
Or to my feeIings concerning
the events on this isIand
?
to which I am confined
WeII, both, reaIIy.
I'm going to have to phone
Miss Lemon today
.
She wanted a daiIy report
You may teII to her
that I am not sure.
Madame Stuart!
Do you depart
for a trip on the sea?
Mr. Poirot!
Captain Hastings! HeIIo!
Yes, I thought I'd take
a cruise round to Pixy Cove!
But pIease
don't teII anyone that!
?
Madame
ARLENA: WeII, everyone here
just has to foIIow me around
.
And for once
,,
I want to be aIone.
POIROT: Jamais.
That I do not beIieve
,.
You think she's going
to meet someone?
It is possibIe, yes.
Oh, excuse me, sir.
Oh. Do you mind
coming back Iater?
I've some
important work to do
.
Leave the door open
It's a bit stuffy in here.
[Typewriter keys dacking]
?
- Are you ready
- Yes.
Let's go then.
[GuIIs caIIing]
Mr. Poirot!
Oh MademoiseIIe Brewster
,.
Something very strange
just happened
.
What is that mademoiseIIe
,?
WeII, I just got back
from my bike ride --
quick five miIes up
and down the coast --
?
would you beIieve it
Someone took a pot shot
at me with a bottIe!
A bottIe?
I think it was a bottIe chucked
,
out of one of the windows.
Where did this take pIace
,
mademoiseIIe?
On the steps
at the side of the hoteI
.
11:15.
- I'd better get changed
.
- Comment?
I'm pIaying tennis at 12:00.
I'd better go and get ready
.
,?
Do you need anything Poirot
Non, merci.
Merci, mon ami.
HASTINGS: Morning.
Morning.
You haven't seen, uh...?
Sorry?
It doesn't matter
.
Um I thought I'd go for a row
,
round the isIand
.
I don't suppose you'd care
to come, Mr. Poirot?
Non, non, merci.
Absolument, non.
Poirot and the sea
,
they are not compatibIe.
I'II come with you.
Mrs. CastIe says that rowing
is very good
for building body tone
.
You can have the oars, then.
[Laughs]
How is it?
It's warm.
You should come in
.
I'm not reaIIy a big swimmer.
Do you have the time?
Hold on
.
It's a quarter to.
Didn't you say you
?
had tennis at 12:00
I'm going to have to run
and get changed
.
WiII you be aII right
on your own?
I'II be fine Mrs Redfern
,..
[Typewriter keys dacking]
Look, there's someone
on Pixy Cove.
EMILY:
Looks Iike Mrs. MarshaII.
So it does
.
We're not going
to Iand here are we
,?
We've got pIenty of time.
Just thought I'd say heIIo
.
ArIena!
EMILY: She's asIeep.
I dunno
.
ArIena?
ArIena!
You aII right?
My God!
She's dead!
She's been strangIed!
Are you sure?
There's no puIse.
She's not breathing.
We have to get the poIice.
You mustn't touch anything!
I know, but one of us has to
stay here with the body.
?
Who would do this
Who would do this!
I don't want to stay
.
You wait here.
I'II go.
Right.
There's a constabIe
at Leathercombe Bay.
No! Poirot!
Fetch Mr. Poirot.
He'II know what to do
.
I can't manage that Iadder
I'II go by boat.
The current's with me.
- I'II be back as soon as I can.
- But just go!
Mr. MarshaII?
[Water running]
Kenneth.
I'm the first to arrive.
After me, yes.
?
Did you get it done
What?
- Your typing.
- Oh, yes.
Ah.
Hastings.
Hastings, what time is it?
It's just coming up to 12:00.
Why?
CHRISTINE: Not Iate, am I?
No. ExactIy on time.
Mr. Poirot!
Hastings!
It is exactIy as I feared
.
HASTINGS: What is it?
DARNLEY: Thank goodness!
It is ArIena Stuart!
She's dead
....
,?
Right where's the body
It's over there, sir.
Right.
Where's the boat?
StrangIed that's for sure
,.
And a pretty powerfuI pair
of hands
.
Must've been a man.
I am aIso of that opinion,
Chief Inspector.
WeII, we're Iucky,
in some ways.
This is a smaII isIand
.
We know exactIy
when the body was discovered
,
and the time of death
could onIy have been about
10 or 20 minutes before.
It should be easy enough to
pinpoint where everyone was.
Where were you?
AII right.
So what kind of a woman was
,
she, then, this ArIena Stuart?
A very fIirtatious one.
She was carrying on outrageousIy
with Patrick Redfern
.
- He was the chap who found her
- Yes.
You said she was married
,
Poirot.
Did her husband
know what was going on?
Oh, yes, Chief Inspector.
It was most certain
that Mr. Kenneth MarshaII
was aware of the behavior
of his wife.
JAPP: WeII, there's a motive
for you, if ever there was one.
POIROT:
Chief Inspector, voilà.
JAPP: Spectades.
[Grunts]
A man's.
Or perhaps of a boy.
I'm sorry.
There's nothing I can do
.
The hoteI is dosed,
the whoIe isIand is dosed
.
You're going
to have to Ieave.
MAN: But we've
onIy just arrived
.
What's going on here, Sergeant?
These two men came over here
on that tractor thing, sir.
They say they're bird watchers
.
We're reguIar visitors.
You have no right to stop us.
We have every right, sir.
I'm pursuing a murder
investigation,
and nobody enters or Ieaves
this isIand untiI I say so.
But we have --
Take them back
to the mainIand Sergeant
,.
Yes, sir.
Come on.
What are you Iooking for,
Poirot?
Chief Inspector, the two
arrivaIs that we saw just now.
?
The bird watchers
Yes Did you notice something
.
about them that was strange?
No.
I did.
They had no binocuIars
.
Très bien, Hastings.
You begin, at Iast, to Iearn.
Voilà.
You see?
Yes, a piece of broken gIass.
Somebody threw a bottIe
at EmiIy Brewster this morning.
From what would
you say has this come?
?
A medicine bottIe
And it contained some Iiquid
that was brown.
But it has no odor
.
I'm so shocked
I'm...
I don't know what to say
.
ArIena...
It's unbeIievabIe.
?
Who would want to kiII her
How Iong had you been married
,
Mr. MarshaII?
- Four years.
- HappiIy?
Yes.
If you pIease,
Monsieur MarshaII,
what is your opinion
?
of Monsieur Redfern
I have no opinion of him.
And yet his reIationship
with your wife...
There was no reIationship.
That's aII just hoteI gossip.
Nothing more!
When was the Iast time
you saw Mrs. MarshaII?
After breakfast.
I Iooked into her room
.
?
You had separate rooms
Yes.
It was about 10:00.
She said she was
going down to the beach
.
Oh, that's right.
We met her just after 10:00.
And what of your movements
,
Monsieur MarshaII?
I had some Ietters to write
.
I stayed up here
typing 'tiI midday
.
Then I went down
to pIay tennis.
That was when I heard the news
.
One finaI question, if you
pIease, Monsieur MarshaII.
Do you recognize these?
Yes, they're LioneI's.
?
Where did you get them
It is of no matter.
Could you pIease
show us
to the room of your wife?
JAPP:
WeII, there's not much here.
I don't think
you'II find anything
in any of those
bottIes, Poirot.
But a bottIe was propeIIed
from this hoteI,
Chief Inspector.
Et oui it could have
,
come from this room.
JAPP: What makes you
so sure it was thrown?
Maybe it was just dropped
.
I say!
A teIegram to ArIena.
From New York.
Dated three days ago
.
Go on.
"Send the money now or you wiII
,
Iose a great deaI. Nathan."
That's it.
Nathan, that rings
some sort of beII.
It was the name
of the young man
with whom she danced at
...
your restaurant, Hastings?
- EI Ranchero.
- Oui.
Sounds a bit threatening
.
I wouldn't mind taIking to him
But if he's in America...
WeII, for me, I prefer
to speak to LioneI MarshaII.
You can't want
to ask me any questions.
I mean I didn't have anything
,
to do with it.
I don't know anything
.
Can you teII us
your movements this morning?
Yes.
I had breakfast
.
I went to the Iibrary.
?
HASTINGS: On the mainIand
Yes.
I am revising for my exams.
Chemistry.
When I came back,
I bumped into Mrs Redfern
..
WeII, she saw the book,
so she can vouch for me.
Hmm. Go on.
She invited me to go swim
with her at GuII Cove.
I swam untiI exactIy 11:45.
How can you be so sure
of the time?
She asked me
and I Iooked at my watch
.
I had another swim
and went back to the hoteI
.
There was a program
on the wireIess,
and I thought I was
going to miss it,
but actuaIIy,
it was onIy 12:10
when I arrived
.
Monsieur LioneI,
this is not easy
for you, I know, but...
if you pIease could you
,
describe your feeIings
for your stepmother?
She was aII right.
You can think of no one
?
who would wish to kiII her
JAPP: Any heIp
you can give us, LioneI.
WeII onIy Mrs Redfern
.....
I mean, boy!
You onIy had to Iook at the way
her husband was aII over ArIena
.
I bet she'd
have wanted to kiII her
.
Not that she had it in her
You mean, she isn't vioIent?
LIONEL: Yes.
Is that aII?
Can I go now?
Pardon one Iast question
,.
If you pIease, I beIieve
that these are yours?
Yes. They're
my old spectades
.
But your old spectades?
Yes I had to have
,
a new prescription,
but I keep those
for emergencies.
?
Where did you find them
Oh, no, no, it is of no matter.
Thank you very much.
You may go now.
That's not a job
I particuIarIy enjoy,
interviewing
a 17-year-old boy
.
Yes.
But a boy with the hands
the size of a man.
Excusez-moi, mademoiselle.
Yes, sir?
You are aware, are you not, that
we are investigating the murder
this morning of ArIena Stuart?
Yes, sir.
It's a terribIe business.
I stiII can't beIieve it.
And you are responsibIe
for the deaning of the rooms
this morning?
?
Between and 10:00 and 12:00
Yes, sir.
MademoiseIIe, could
you teII to us whether
you heard or saw anything
out of the usuaI?
Not reaIIy, sir.
There was no one around
,
apart from Mr. MarshaII.
He was in his room.
?
Did you see him
I did see him about 10 15
:.
That's when I went in
to make the beds.
I didn't see him
again after that.
So he could have
Ieft the room.
No sir I heard him
,,.
He was typing.
MademoiseIIe have you observed
,
in any of the rooms
a bottIe which is now missing,
or which contains, perhaps,
something strange?
WeII...Mrs. MarshaII
has perfume bottIes.
And Mr Lane
....
HASTINGS: The vicar.
His bathroom's fuII of bottIes.
Ah Could you show
.
to us his bathroom?
JAPP: Where is Lane?
ApparentIy, he's visiting
friends on the mainIand
.
Chief Inspector,
what is that Iiquid
that is brown?
Morphine.
Is there anything eIse, sir?
Non, merci, mademoiselle.
UnIess mademoiseIIe
,?
UnIess there was something
that you observed
that was unexpIained
,
or curious.
Something that was different
from the other days
.
Not that I can think of.
ActuaIIy,
there was one thing.
But it can't be important,
though.
No, go on.
WeII, just before 12:00,
I thought I heard someone
running a bath.
And it did strike me as odd
,
someone having a bath
at that time.
Whose bath was it?
I couldn't teII you sir
,.
Somewhere on this fIoor.
But it could have been anywhere
.
If the bath was run
just before 12:00,
that's 20 minutes
after the body was discovered
.
Exactement, Hastings.
It is strange, n'est-ce pas?
Broken bottIes, running baths...
the troubIe with you, Poirot,
is you aIways have to make
everything so compIicated.
Madame Redfern
.
Oh, Mr. Poirot,
I was waiting for you.
I suppose you want to know
my movements this morning.
S'il vous plaît, madame.
If you would commence
from the moment you woke up.
CHRISTINE: I had breakfast
.
- I met LioneI.
- JAPP: LioneI MarshaII.
He'd just come back
from the Iibrary.
CHRISTINE: That's right.
I suggested that he come
with me whiIe I was sketching.
We stayed together
at GuII Cove
untiI exactIy
a quarter to 12:00.
He had a watch
and he told me the time
.
I then went back to the hoteI,
got changed
,
and arrived at the tennis courts
at 12:00 on the dot.
And that was when we heard
.
And had you at any time seen
,,
ArIena Stuart this morning?
No, I hadn't.
I didn't want to
.
Were you surprised
?
at her death
Surprised
No.
I was shocked but I wasn't
,
exactIy surprised.
A woman of that sort is mixed up
in everything that's sordid.
BIackmaiI, jeaIousy,
vioIence...
What do you mean
,
bIackmaiI?
WeII, it was just
something I overheard
.
JAPP: What?
Last night, Miss Stuart
received a teIephone caII
.
Oh, that's right.
It was just before dinner
.
WeII I happened
,
to be passing,
and I overheard
what she was saying.
I suppose it was wrong of me
to eavesdrop
.
No, no, pIease.
Someone was asking
her for money.
She said she couldn't
get any more.
She said she was going to teII
her husband everything.
Those were her very words
.
?
But didn't you hear a name
I mean,
was it a man or a woman?
I have no idea
.
I didn't want to be seen
,
especiaIIy by her,
so I hurried on in to dinner
.
But it was bIackmaiI,
I'm sure of it.
JAPP: BIackmaiI!
That must tie in with
the teIegram you found
.
Nathan, the man in New York.
- So it might seem.
- But it doesn't make any sense
.
ArIena didn't have
,?
any money did she
Au contraire, Chief Inspector.
She was a woman of weaIth
in her own right.
Oh the Erskine scandaI
,.
Sir Roger Erskine.
ApparentIy,
he Ieft her a fortune.
Oh. It wiII be interesting
to know how much of it is Ieft.
It wiII indeed
,
Chief Inspector.
She must have a Iawyer
or a bank manager.
I suppose we could
ask her husband
.
No, no, no, Chief Inspector.
I think it better
that we do not inform
Monsieur MarshaII of this.
Miss Lemon, she wiII make
the inquiries for me.
I must teIephone
to her at once.
[TeIephone rings]
MISS LEMON: Yes, Mr. Poirot,
I'm stiII here.
How are you?
Oh, Mr. Poirot, it wasn't meant
to be a busman's hoIiday
.
Very weII.
Right.
I'II get on to it
first thing tomorrow.
In normaI circumstances,
Miss Lemon,
the information
you're requesting
would be considered
confidentiaI
.
I quite understand
,
Mr AppIegood
..
However, I have
to say that the bank
was aIready graveIy concerned
about Mrs. MarshaII,
and given the circumstances
,
of her death
and the fact that Mr Poirot
.
was invoIved...
Six weeks ago, Mrs. MarshaII
came to my office,
and instructed me to withdraw
a very Iarge sum of money
from her account.
The money was to be paid
in bearer bonds.
Did she say what
the money was for?
I'm afraid not
.
I did try to eIicit from her
what her intentions were,
but she said it was
her own private business,
and I feIt unabIe
to press her further.
How did she seem
,
.?
Mr AppIegood
Was she nervous
or afraid?
Neither.
She was determined
....
That would be the best word
to describe her
.
I don't suppose
you can teII me
how much of her money
?
was invoIved
I don't see that it makes
any difference now
.
We're taIking aII of it.
Just about
her entire fortune.
.?
Mr Redfern
I'd wondered when you'd
be coming taIk to me.
Are you the poIice?
JAPP: Chief Inspector Japp.
ScotIand Yard.
To be honest sir I find
,,
it a IittIe strange,
your carrying on Iike this
as if nothing had happened
.
?
What eIse am I meant to do
The whoIe thing's
so bIoody horribIe
.
You're forgetting
I was the one who found her
.
I am just trying to put
it out of my mind.
Mr Redfern did you anticipate
.,
to find yesterday
Madame MarshaII
on the beach at Pixy Cove?
No, as a matter of fact,
I was Iooking for her when
I met you on the terrace.
But I didn't know
where she'd gone
.
Why were you
Iooking for her, sir?
WeII, it's not easy
to expIain.
Au contraire, Monsieur Redfern.
To expIain,
I think, it is most simpIe.
You were in Iove
with Madame MarshaII
.
Not in Iove.
Infatuated
.
I hope you reaIize, sir, that
this "infatuation" of yours
could very weII be the reason
for Mrs. MarshaII's death.
?
What do you mean
WeII if her husband
,
had caught wind of it
...
What?
?
He'd have strangIed her
Kenneth's not the sort.
What about your wife?
Christine had nothing
to do with it
.
If she was going to kiII anyone,
she probabIy would've kiIIed me
.
And anyway it's impossibIe
,.
What makes you so sure of that,
monsieur?
Because I saw the body
,
that's why.
And it had to be a man
.
I saw what had been done
to her neck.
It was a man's hands
.
You know it and so do I
,.
But I onIy want
to go to the mainIand
for a coupIe of hours,
just to dear my head.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I'II take that from you.
What?!
Mr. Poirot!
Is it reaIIy true that
?
no one can Ieave the isIand
I'm afraid I'm keeping
everyone here
untiI I've compIeted
my investigations.
MademoiseIIe Brewster
,
there is something that
I do wish to ask you.
EMILY: Oh, yes?
We spoke together
of ArIena Stuart
the day before her body
,
it was discovered
.
Yes I was wondering when
,
you'd ask me about that
.
And you said
...
"I'd be happy to stick
a hat pin in her."
I wasn't being serious.
A year ago I invested money
,
in a pIay...she was starring.
But after the first performance,
she just waIked out.
So, you Iost your investment.
AII of it.
Of course I was annoyed but
,,...
It was a stupid thing to say
.
I reaIIy didn't mean it
An unfortunate coincidence
.
But I was nowhere near the beach
when it happened.
And Mr Redfern
.
was with me
when we found her
.
It must have been a great shock
to you to discover the body.
It was horribIe.
At first,
she didn't Iook dead
.
She just Iooked
as if she was sunbathing.
?
But then you moved more dose
EMILY: And I saw at once
.
There was something unnaturaI
about the way she was Iying.
Her arms...
And underneath her tan --
She had a IoveIy tan
before she even arrived here --
there was
a sort of paIeness...
The paIeness of death
.
Yes.
I'II never forget it.
POIROT: Monsieur BIatt.
Is the tractor Ieaving?
Because if it is,
I'm going home now.
I'm sorry, sir, no one
is to Ieave the isIand
.
- What?
- They've just told me the same
.
[Laughs]
You can't stop me.
I'II take me own boat
if I have to.
I wouldn't try that
if I were you, sir.
Monsieur BIatt I would be
,
interested to know
why it was your boat
was anchored dose to the beach
at Pixy Cove
the day before
ArIena Stuart died
.
It wasn't.
We both saw it.
WeII...
maybe I went for a swim.
I don't remember
where I was, reaIIy.
I stopped
and went for a swim
.
How Iong do you propose
to keep us here?
As Iong as it takes.
DARNLEY:
I can't beIieve it!
A second time!
Why is it that
when you're around
,
peopIe seem to drop
Iike fIies?
I met MademoiseIIe DarnIey
when I was in Egypt.
May I introduce Chief Inspector
Japp of ScotIand Yard
.
?
JAPP: How do you do
Let's get straight down to
brass tacks, Chief Inspector.
PIease sit down
.
POIROT:
Merci, mademoiselle.
I expect you want
to know my movements
at the time of the crime.
JAPP: If you don't mind
,
Miss DarnIey.
I've written them down
.
I thought it would save time
JAPP: Thank you.
"Breakfast at 9:00.
Left the hoteI
at around haIf past
.
WaIked over to Sunny Ledge
,
arriving about 9:45."
?
Sunny Ledge
It's on top of the diffs.
You get a good view
of Pixy Cove.
You can see the whoIe beach,
the cave, everything.
And before you ask me yes
,,,
I did see ArIena arrive
in that boat of hers.
But that's aII I saw.
Hmm.
You returned
to the hoteI at 10 to 12:00
and arrived
at the tennis court
10 minutes Iater.
Is that it?
I'm afraid so
.
MademoiseIIe DarnIey
,
a moment ago,
you mentioned the view of
the beach at Pixy Cove.
You remarked that
?
you could see the cave
Yes it's quite hard to make out
,
the entrance from there.
It's conceaIed
.
But you can see it.
Yes.
So this cave it does
,,,
indeed, exist.
Miss Brewster mentioned
it the other evening.
Of course, it exists.
It's over here.
POIROT: Merci.
Oh, Hastings, this kiIIer
could not have suffered as I do
from le mal de mer.
- Sorry?
- The sickness of the sea.
Ah. He'd need
to be pretty fit, too.
POIROT: It is true.
Down the Iadder
,
across the beach and back up
again in a hurry.
That narrows it down
.
Whew.
?
MademoiseIIe
That's the entrance there.
Right. You wait here,
Miss DarnIey.
Oh.
JAPP:
It's a cave, aII right.
HASTINGS: Good Lord!
WeII, there's nothing here.
Not to see, there is nothing,
Chief Inspector.
But to smeII...
[Sniffs]
?
Seaweed
Perfume.
Hastings, you recaII that
in the bedroom of ArIena Stuart
,
there was a bottIe of perfume
?
that I smeIIed
You mean, it's the same?
Oui.
There's some footprints.
FIat, no heeI.
Canvas...
Beach shoes, or something.
To where do these footprints
,?
Iead Chief Inspector
JAPP: Ah it's a dead end
,.
Wait a minute!
?
Sandwiches
I do not think so
.
This is heroin.
That changes everything,
Poirot.
Drugs, that's what's
at the bottom of this.
Perhaps, Chief Inspector.
No doubt about it
if you ask me.
HASTINGS: Why are we going
to the mainIand Poirot
,?
What's so important
to the case?
It is not important,
Hastings.
It is vitaI.
Here you are, sir.
Voilà, Hastings.
The IittIe grey ceIIs, they
are the army of NapoIeon.
You mean they march
on their stomach?
For you, sir.
Thank you.
You had any thoughts
then, Poirot?
Oui, it is true,
Chief Inspector,
that the discovery of a Iarge
quantity of heroin
dose to the pIace where
ArIena Stuart was murdered
would indicate that this was
the motive for the crime.
HASTINGS: You said you smeIIed
her perfume in the cave.
- Oui.
- WeII, there you are, then.
She went into the cave,
stumbIed on the heroin
,
reaIized there was some sort
of drugs ring
operating on the isIand
,
someone strangIed her
to siIence her.
No.
One question, Chief Inspector.
The cave, it is dark
,?
and unpIeasant no
?
Why did she enter
Was she indeed
?
being bIackmaiIed
AIso, what was in the bottIe
that was thrown
?
at MademoiseIIe Brewster
And how did the spectades
of LioneI MarshaII come to be
at the bottom of the Iadder?
And yes aIso I wonder
,,
what was in the book
that he was reading.
It's good to see you
back on form, Poirot.
JAPP: [Laughs] One heIping
of spotted dick
and you'II probabIy soIve it
.
[Laughs]
LioneI MarshaII -- a young man
staying on the isIand
.
Let me have a Iook.
He borrowed a book
yesterday morning.
Ah.
Oh, yes,
of course, I remember now.
I thought it was
a rather strange choice,
but he said it was
for a homework project.
And the name of the book
,
if you pIease, madame?
"Dangerous ChemicaIs
and Poisons."
- Oh.
- Excuse me.
Those two!
?
What are they stiII doing here
WeII, perhaps they're taking out
a book on bird watching.
It aII begins to make sense.
JAPP: What, you mean
LioneI MarshaII?
WeII, there was obviousIy
was no Iove Iost
between him
and his stepmother
.
You mean he was thinking
of poisoning her?
And in the end,
he used his bare hands
.
But he is onIy 17.
Hastings,
is that not Monsieur Lane?
HASTINGS: WeII, it's been
a whiIe since he saw him.
He wasn't at the hoteI
Iast night.
That's a chemist shop.
And he had drugs
of some sort in his room.
Allons! Monsieur Lane!
Mr. Poirot!
You have heard about
?
the events on the isIand
Yes.
DreadfuI
.
They were taIking
about it in the shop.
Perhaps you'II return
now to the hoteI?
Yes.
We'II come with you.
I was on the mainIand aII day
.
I wasn't anywhere near her.
I couldn't have
had anything to do with it
.
Why didn't you return here
Iast night, sir?
I was having dinner
with a friend --
the Bishop of Exmouth.
It was Iate so he suggested
,
I stay the night.
And for what purpose
have you come here
to this isIand
,
Monsieur Lane?
I've told you
.
I've been iII.
I needed a rest for my nerves
.
?
And you're a vicar
I was.
The church of Saint Mathew
at BIackridge, in Kent.
I had to Ieave
.
JAPP: Why was that?
There was a scandaI
.
My wife...
You see...
She Ieft me.
She ran away with a member
of my congregation.
She was a wicked woman
.
She should have
been punished.
I've got a question for you,
if you don't mind
,
Mr. Lane.
Are you, by any chance,
?
taking some sort of drugs
I have an opiate
prescribed by my doctor
.
It's for my nerves.
But it's perfectIy IegaI,
Chief Inspector.
I've done nothing wrong
.
An opiate?
I wonder.
Did you not remark
,
Chief Inspector,
the viIIage
of which he spoke...
BIackridge
.
BIackridge?
Hey, wait a minute!
AIice Corrigan.
It was a murder unsoIved
,
n'est ce-pas?
JAPP: About two years ago.
She was strangIed too
,.
HASTINGS:
You think there's a Iink?
WeII, it's a bit
of a coincidence --
the reverend comes from a pIace
with an unsoIved murder,
and now the same thing
happens here.
WeII perhaps someone should ask
,
a few more questions.
Yet another task for
the inimitabIe Miss Lemon.
[Train whistIe bIows]
[Conductor's whistIe bIows]
Thank you.
Miss Lemon?
Chief Inspector.
Weston.
CharIes Weston.
Do come this way.
[Departing train chugging]
So, how is Mr. Poirot?
He was meant
to be having a rest.
I'd very much Iike to meet him
.
Of course,
I've heard a Iot about him
.
There's the Church
of Saint Mathew.
This is where
the body was found
.
Ugh StrangIed
..
Yes.
She was found by a game's
mistress, Jane MartindaIe.
She was cyding in the area.
Must have rather spoiIed
her hoIiday.
She reported it to us
.
What can you teII me
about the dead girI?
AIice Corrigan.
She was 27.
Engaged to be married
.
She was a weaIthy woman
in own right.
We think that might
have been the motive.
You thought she'd been
kiIIed by her fiancé
.
Edward DeveriII
Oh, yes.
He inherited everything
.
But the body was discovered
at 10:15
in the middIe
of the morning church service,
and he was on the London train
at the time.
Non-stop to BIackridge
.
And we had a dozen witnesses
who saw him
get on and get off
.
It couldn't have been him
So it was never soIved
,.
WESTON: And never wiII be
.
UnIess Mr. Poirot
has some new Iight
to shed on the matter
.
I think you can expect pIenty
of new Iight,
now Mr Poirot is invoIved
..
Chief Inspector?
Yes, sir?
I'm Major Barry
and I was wondering
...
if I might have a word
with you.
?
About the murder
WeII I was wondering
,
how Iong you expect
this investigation
of yours to continue?
WeII that's hard to say sir
,,.
I see.
Because I...
Never mind
.
What was that?
I have no idea
.
,?
Are you ready Captain Hastings
Yes. Do you think this pIan
of Poirot's is going to work?
I hope so.
He's teIIing them now.
So, when are you going
aIIow us off the isIand,
,.?
and Iet us go home Mr Poirot
I have aIready asked
Chief Inspector Japp
to open up
this isIand once again
.
Oh!
ReaIIy?
POIROT: Oh, yes,
Monsieur BIatt.
The new guests, they are now
permitted to arrive
.
Good
WeII, I'm going,
if you don't mind
.
I've had enough
of hanging around
.
?
Have you worked it out yet
This is a case most compIicated
,
MademoiseIIe Brewster
.
DARNLEY: But,
?
you must have some idea
Et bien, mademoiselle,
I am a man very simpIe.
I aIways indine to the beIief
that the person
who is most obvious is the one
who committed the crime.
And in this case, there
is indicated very dearIy
...
one person.
Who?
But there is what
you might caII the snag, huh?
Because it seems impossibIe
for this person to have
committed the crime
.
JAPP:
So, Poirot was right.
HASTINGS: As usuaI.
,?
Come bird watching have we
Don't think we'II
find many birds
nesting in there, wiII you?
?
What do you want
We haven't done anything wrong
,
you know?
Oh, no?
I suppose that depends
on what's inside of that box
you've just taken.
And I think we aII know
what that is don't we
,?
AII right.
Get back!
JAPP: Don't be daft!
You're not going
to use that.
I've got men
aII over this isIand
.
You're Iying!
Shoot them --
shoot them both,
and Iet's get out of here!
I am a Chief Inspector
from ScotIand Yard!
Put that gun down!
Do it!
Wait!
Ah!
Are you aII right?
JACK: Damn you!
Don't Iet him get away!
Come on you, on your feet!
JAPP: Stop him!
I'm with the Home Office.
Seconded to ScotIand Yard
,
for drug inquiries
.
What, you mean,
you're one of us?
?
Why didn't someone teII me
Sorry about that -- had
to keep it under wraps
.
Hold on to him there!
I am sorry I tried to warn you
off the way I did, Mr. Poirot.
I've been watching
this pIace for months,
and I was afraid you were going
to bIow the whoIe operation.
It is of no matter, Major Barry.
Anyway, I've got them,
that's aII that matters.
Your two "bird watchers "
.
[Laughs]
Oh they had a good thing
,
going for them down here
.
The stuff coming in
from the continent.
?
But how did it get here
Oh, that, Hastings,
is most simpIe.
BLATT: What do you
?
think you're doing!
You can't treat me Iike this!
This is an outrage!
POIROT: Oh, the game,
it is over, Monsieur BIatt.
And there Hastings
,,
is the answer to your question.
It is Monsieur BIatt who speaks
of DeauviIIe and of Nice,
but chooses to saiI here.
And of course
,,
he wears the saiIing shoes
made of canvas
.
The footprints
in the cave!
POIROT: Oui, c'est ça.
The heroin, it is carried
from France with the red saiI
which signaIs to the mainIand
that it arrives.
And the white saiI
is the "aII dear."
Oui.
BARRY: You have got it in one,
Mr. Poirot.
Oh, we've known about
this gang for some time.
We just couldn't pinpoint
the pIace of entry.
Take him away!
Go on.
JAPP: Wait a minute, Poirot.
Are you seriousIy suggesting
that aII this had nothing to do
?
with the death of ArIena Stuart
POIROT:
So it would now appear
.
But you said she went into the
cave you smeIIed her perfume
,.
That is indeed what I thought
,
Chief Inspector.
But then the question becomes,
why did ArIena Stuart
enter the cave?
WeII perhaps she was hiding
,
from someone.
Hastings, once again,
you arrive at an expIanation
which makes everything dear!
Not to me it doesn't
,.
You mean she was afraid
,
of someone?
I mean, Hastings, that there
is eviI on this isIand,
and the murder
that took pIace here
was the work of a mind
that was briIIiant.
But there was one thing that
the kiIIer did not expect --
the mind of HercuIe Poirot
.
Et bien, now is the time
for these two minds to meet
and the truth at Iast
must come to Iight.
POIROT: I congratuIate you,
Miss Lemon.
You have achieved
a great success.
JAPP: So, you think that
the deaths of ArIena Stuart
,
and this AIice Corrigan
are definiteIy Iinked?
Of that I am sure,
Chief Inspector.
Both women were young,
both strangIed,
one with a fiancé,
the other a husband
who could not have possibIy
committed the crime.
Edward DeveriII
because he was on a train,
Kenneth MarshaII because he was
typing Ietters in his room.
Oui, c'est ça.
Everyone's gathering
in the dining room Poirot
,.
Bon.
The time, it has come.
[PIaces gIass on tabIe]
So...
Let us go.
Mesdames and Messieurs
,
we have aII come here to this
hoteI for the reasons
of heaIth, exercise,
for the hoIiday
...
and for murder
.
I, myseIf, was here on account
of an iIIness,
but it was not my body
that was put to exercise, no,
it was the IittIe grey ceIIs.
How was this crime,
so seemingIy impossibIe,
in fact committed
,?
And who among us
is responsibIe
for the death
of ArIena Stuart?
Do you know?
Oui!
Bien sûr, mademoiselle.
HercuIe Poirot, he knows aII.
La pauvre Arlena.
To Monsieur Lane,
as he watched her swimming
on the beach,
she was the focus of eviI, no?
Of eviI under the sun
.
LANE: You don't have
to be of the church
to recognize eviI,
Mr. Poirot.
I see it there.
I recognize it.
It's reaI.
But...
to my mind
,
the eviI was connected
with ArIena Stuart
in a different way
.
I saw her first, Iast,
and aII of the time
,
as a victim,
eternaI and predestined
.
You mean, she was being
bIackmaiIed.
POIROT: Of that I am not
so sure, Chief Inspector.
CHRISTINE: But I heard
her on the teIephone.
No no no madame
,,,.
You heard onIy onIy one side
of the conversation.
Hastings, do you not recaII
the teIegram that we discovered
?
in the bedroom of ArIena Stuart
Yes, it was from someone
caIIed Nathan.
I say!
It's a teIegram to ArIena
from New York.
Dated three days ago
.
Go on.
"Send the money now or you wiII
Iose a great deaI. Nathan."
To the Chief Inspector Japp,
this man, Nathan,
seemed to be threatening her
.
But to me, he wrote simpIy
a statement of fact.
?
What do you mean
He was an American,
Chief Inspector,
speaking of a great deaI
,
a great business deaI
.
Now, it is my beIief
that he wanted
the money of ArIena Stuart
simpIy to invest.
You mean he wasn't
bIackmaiIing her?
POIROT:
We saw them once, Hastings.
They were together dancing
.
Yet you wiII not dance
,
with a man
who threatens to destroy
your Iife.
?
Nathan LIoyd
Hmm, Monsieur MarshaII?
KENNETH: You're right.
He's a New York stockbroker,
aIthough
not a very reputabIe one.
Oui, c'est ça.
So, this was simpIy
a case of man who was young,
who was how do you say
,,
opportunistic, who saw
ArIena Stuart
exactIy for what she was --
a target,
and a very easy one
.
WeII, she had inherited aII that
money from Sir Roger Erskine.
And now it's aII gone
,
every penny of it.
That's what
her bank manager told me
.
So, are you saying, she sent it
aII to this chap in New York?
No, I say that
this was the weakness
in her that was fataI.
That she was attracted
aIways to men
who took
of her onIy the advantage
.
We were happy together!
[Laughs]
Monsieur MarshaII, you are a man
most gaIIant, n'est-ce pas?
But for you, Iife with
her must have been a torture.
AIso, I beIieve, for your son.
I didn't Iike her but I never
,
made any secret of it
.
No, it was aIso your spectades
that were discovered
beside the Iadder at Pixy Cove
.
At the time of her death
,
you were aIone.
I was swimming
with Mrs Redfern!
.
At a quarter to 12:00, yes.
We have onIy your word for it
that that was indeed the time
.
Madame Redfern
could not see the watch
.
Suppose it was onIy 11:30, hmm?
That would have given you
sufficient time,
after she had departed
for her tennis, to run
to the Iadder dimb down --
,
- No!
Leave him aIone damn you!
,
He's onIy a boy!
And you have no aIibi for the
time that your wife was kiIIed!
I told you I was typing
,.
You were heard to type yes
,,
but you were never seen!
From the very start,
it was my beIief
that one person aIone
must be responsibIe
for this crime.
And each person here
in this room
wished the death
of ArIena Stuart.
I didn't!
Yes, you did --
she was the person
who stood between you
and Monsieur MarshaII
.
The son aIso,
who studies poisons
,
wished to see his father
set free.
I never went near her!
MademoiseIIe Brewster
Iost a great deaI of money
because of her and you
,,
Madame Redfern beIieved
,
you were in danger
of Iosing your husband
.
Yes, but I didn't.
I mean I couldn't!
,
[Gasps]
I had no reason to kiII her
.
Oh.
Monsieur Lane...
To you, she was a woman of eviI,
just as your wife.
And you aIso wished
to see her punished.
No!
So, who was it then, Poirot?
It was the person
who she went to meet that day
on the beach at Pixy Cove.
I thought I'd take a cruise
round to Pixy Cove
.
But pIease,
don't teII anyone that
.
?
Madame
ARLENA: WeII, everyone here
just has to foIIow me around
.
And for once
,
I want to be aIone.
Both Hastings
and I saw quite dearIy
...
She was on her way
to an assignation.
Oui.
And an assignation with you
...
Monsieur Redfern
.
No!
POIROT: Oh, yes.
I knew you for what you were
from the moment
I first saw you --
a wastreI, cheating
and defrauding women of weaIth
.
Like Nathan LIoyd
and aII the other young men
who were drawn to her --
she was your prey!
To heII with you!
You've got it aII wrong!
It can't be Redfern -- he was
the one who discovered her
.
SeemingIy so, yes,
Chief Inspector.
But what if the the body
that was discovered
by Monsieur Redfern
on the beach that day
,,
was not, in fact,
ArIena Stuart?
EMILY:
Oh, but it was, Mr. Poirot.
I saw her myseIf.
No MademoiseIIe Brewster you
,,
saw what you were meant to see.
And I wiII teII
to you aII how it was -- a crime
of the most ingenious.
At 9:30, Christine Redfern
makes the arrangement
to go swimming
with Lionel Marshall.
- Where have you been?
- I went to the mainIand.
POlROT: She sees the book.
So I see.
She knows of his dislike
of his stepmother,
and it is not hard to see what
is going on in his mind.
?
Why don't you come with me
You could have a swim.
POlROT: And that was a bonus
that was unexpected.
AII right.
I'II meet you here
in an hour from now.
10:30.
POlROT: So, now the plan
that was pre-prepared
is now set into motion,
and the timing,
it must be precise.
First, Madame Redfern
returns to her room
and applies to her skin,
that is pale,
some makeup which is dark.
She will now appear
to have the suntan.
First, she must dispose
of the evidences,
which will be lost
in the undergrowth
outside of the hotel.
But it was a mistake
to throw the bottle
out of the window,
because there
happens to be walking
dose to the hotel
at that time
Mademoiselle Brewster,
who sees the bottle fall.
lt was a remnant of this bottle
that l found,
containing some liquid
that was brown.
You see?
But now Christine Redfern
can keep her appointment
with Lionel Marshall.
She leaves the hotel
wearing the beach dothes
that are very loose-fitting
and which completely cover
the make-up she has put on.
- Morning.
- Good morning
.
- Have you seen...?
- I'm sorry?
It doesn't matter
.
POlROT: At the same time,
Monsieur Patrick Redfern
suggests to me that he does not
know the whereabouts
of Arlena Stuart.
And so to Gull Cove.
While Lionel Marshall
swims in the sea,
it is simple for
Madame Redfern
to steal his spectades,
and to alter the time
on his watch.
- How is it?
- It's warm.
Do you have the time?
It's a quarter to.
But is was not quarter to 12:00.
No.
It was no more than
haIf past 11:00.
You told me so no
,?
You thought you would be Iate
for a program
that you wished to hear
on the wireIess.
That's right.
But, in fact, it was
onIy a IittIe after 12:00
when I got back.
So now Madame Redfern
,
she has much to do
and has gained herseIf
additionaI time
with which to do it
.
First,
she returns the watch
to the time that is correct.
This is unlikely to be noticed
by Lionel Marshall,
which is indeed the case.
Then, she runs across
the island to Pixy Cove,
which, of course,
requires great speed
and stamina.
Hastings, you wiII recaII
that she told to us
of her former occupation.
- Oh she said she was a teacher
,.
- Oui.
But what if she was a teacher
of the physicaI education?
Someone for whom such exercise
?
and exertion would be easy
She arrives at the ladder
above Pixy Cove.
Patrick?
Are you there?!
And is careful to ensure
that Arlena Stuart sees her.
However, Arlena had made
a secret rendezvous
with Patrick Redfern,
and his wife is the last person
she wishes to see.
But Arlena Stuart
and Patrick Redfern,
they have made a plan.
lf Madame Redfern
should happen to appear,
she would hide in the cave.
The mouth of this cave,
it is very narrow.
lt has no view of the entrance
to the cove,
or that part of the beach
where Madame Redfern
is changing,
hidden by the rocks.
And so everything is prepared
for the next stage of the plan.
The timing,
it has to be perfect.
Patrick Redfern has already
begun his tour of the island
with Mademoiselle Brewster.
Look, there's someone
on Pixy Cove.
EMILY:
Looks Iike Mrs. MarshaII.
POlROT: And so to the discovery
of the body.
With a hair that is false,
the Chinese hat,
and the make-up that is brown,
she will resemble
very much Arlena Stuart.
She's dead!
She's been strangIed!
Are you sure?
WeII...
There's no puIse.
She's not breathing.
We have to get the poIice.
You mustn't touch anything.
Oh, no, no, no.
But one of us has to stay here
with the body.
He chose you,
MademoiseIIe Brewster
,
to go with him in the boat
because he knew that,
Iike the rest of us you would
,
not wish to dimb the Iadder.
It was essentiaI
that you should
return in the boat.
But I could have sworn
it was her.
I reaIIy thought it was ArIena!
Yes. But even so, it was you
who told to me Iater
that you detected a certain
paIeness beneath the tan.
It was
because the tan was fake!
Oui.
And you departed with great
haste to find help, huh,
leaving as you thought
Patrick Redfern
alone with the body.
She's gone.
POlROT: As soon as you were
out of sight,
Monsieur and Madame Redfern
were able to put into action
the next part of their plan.
Christine Redfern
now returns to the ladder.
She drops there the spectades
that she has stolen
from Lionel Marshall.
She knows that he has been
contemplating murder,
and that he wiII be impIicated
.
Et bien,
to the rest of the world,
ArIena Stuart is aIready dead
,
and both Monsieur
and Madame Redfern
have the aIibis that
are beyond dispute
.
But for ArIena Stuart,
her death,
it is stiII to come.
ArIena?
DarIing?
I'm here.
Has she gone?
Christine was here.
I did what you told me
and hid in the cave
.
Forget Christine now.
The beautifuI ArIena.
She was an actress
most accompIished
,
but a woman most susceptibIe.
Men preyed
on her for her money.
Men Iike the American,
Mr Nathan LIoyd but it was
.,
Monsieur Patrick Redfern
who tempted her most of aII
.
Who better to suggest a scheme
of investment for her money
than a journaIist
who worked on the city pages
of the newspapers?
And so she gives to him
aII of her money to invest.
But, of course, there was
no such scheme.
And from that moment
,
her fate it was seaIed
,.
JAPP: He takes the money,
and then he kiIIs her
.
Oui, c'est ça,
Chief Inspector.
And from now the rest
,,,
it is very simpIe.
Christine Redfern
returns to the hotel.
With great haste, she takes
off her outer dothing,
And there now needs only
to be removed from her body
the make-up that is brown.
So, she must take a bath.
And it is this
that is heard by the maid
as she performs her duties.
lt is now 12:00 midday.
And every single task
has now been accomplished.
And neither Monsieur
nor Madame Redfern
could possibly
have committed the murder.
HeIIo.
I'm not Iate, am I?
- No, exactIy on time.
- EMILY: Mr. Poirot!
Mr. Poirot!
It's ArIena Stuart.
She's dead
....
JAPP: WeII,
that's the most deviIish thing
I've ever heard.
Yes, Chief Inspector, it was
,?
indeed unique huh
For the murder it was committed
,
after the time of her death.
But this was not
the first occasion
that they had effected
such a scheme.
The AIice Corrigan affair.
POIROT: Yes, Miss Lemon.
Another woman who was young,
murdered for her money.
But this time, by a fiancé
who could have not
possibIy have been there.
And who was it that
?
discovered the body
A game's mistress.
Absolument.
Again, a teacher
of the physicaI education
.
At that time,
Christine Redfern called
herself Jane Martindale.
And it was she
who at a quarter past 10:00
discovered the body
that could not possibly
have been there.
[Screaming]
[Conductor's whistIe bIows]
The true killer, who called
himself Edward Deverill,
arrives on a London train
at only 20 past 10:00
and hurries to a meeting
that he has arranged
with his fiancée.
Again, the timing,
it has been parfait.
For Alice Corrigan
is strangled
after her body
has supposedly been found.
Strangled by you,
Monsieur Redfern!
JAPP: My God!
Alors Jane MartindaIe
,,
Edward DeveriII
,
Monsieur and Madame Redfern --
a coupIe who preyed on women
who were young and weaIthy.
Mr. Lane,
I know that
you have not been weII,
you have suffered
from the nerves most bad
,
but perhaps,
the evil that you saw
that day on the beach,
it was the same evil
that you glimpsed
in a courtroom
two years before.
MAN: This inquest, therefore,
returns a verdict
of murder by person
or persons unknown.
Yes.
He Iooks different now
.
But it was him.
Très bien,
Monsieur Poirot.
Monsieur.
You...
damned interfering
,...
Iousy IittIe worm!
Patrick!
[Screams]
The face of eviI,
it remains aIways the same.
[Baby cries]
MISS LEMON: So much
for your rest cure, Mr. Poirot.
Yes perhaps you should
,
take up running, Poirot,
or how about tennis?
Obesity is today's
number one kiIIer,
I'm told
.
No, no, no, Hastings.
The diagnosis of the hospitaI
was at fauIt.
My taiIor teIIs to me that
I am a fine figure of a man.
And you'd sooner beIieve
your taiIor
than a medicaIIy
?
quaIified doctor
Mais certainement.
The remedies of my taiIor
are painfuI
onIy to my bank account.
But, to ceIebrate the return
to heaIth of Poirot,
may I suggest a IittIe meaI
together most conviviaI?
HASTINGS: Oh spIendid
,.
We can aII go to EI Ranchero.
I'm afraid not,
Captain Hastings.
What?
I'm sorry, Poirot,
I know you didn't want me
to teII
Captain Hastings yet, but...
TeII me what?
WeII, Poirot's IittIe probIem
was food poisoning.
I don't understand
.
This was not the first case
associated with EI Ranchero
,
Hastings.
It was the 14th.
No!
The Ministry of HeaIth
have dosed it down.
What rot!
How do you know
about this, anyway?
I've asked the Yard
to post an armed guard
around the kitchen area
.
What?!
Just whiIe
they do some more tests
.
But I've got a fortune
tied up in that pIace!
Come, come, come, Hastings,
what is done is done
.
And what is underdone
is underdone
.
Oh! No.
But to heIp you
with your Iosses,
I wiII treat us aII to my
favorite IittIe BeIgian bistro
just around the corner.
And I am pIeased to say
they have never been known
to serve l'eau d'ortie.
?
Load of what
L'eau d'ortie, Chief Inspector.
The water of the nettIe.
[Laughter]
SUBTITLING MADE POSSIBLE BY
RLJ ENTERTAINMENT