[knocking on door]
[in Spanish] Who is it?
[Lázaro] Open the door, fucking Jerónimo.
Seriously?
What?
Like you don't use lotions to look good.
I don't know what the hell's wrong
with everyone in this fucking town.
But I'll tell you one thing, asshole.
You're going to stop
supporting that butch.
[laughs]
Like, seriously, you came all the way
to my house to threaten me?
No, no, that's not how it works, Lázaro.
Because I honestly can support
whoever I want, hmm?
And I don't know why you've got
such a problem with Charly.
Because, at the end of the day,
obviously, your son is the one
who's got what he needs to win.
Because that little witch
is messing around with my daughter.
Now she'll meet the real me.
Either you side with me,
or I'll air your dirty laundry.
Uh...
[Lázaro] Looks can be deceiving.
[Angélica] Baby, who is it?
- Mr. Lázaro, good evening.
- [Lázaro] Good evening, Mrs. Angélica.
Forgive me for coming so late
and for interrupting
your feminine beauty treatment.
Oh, Mr. Lázaro, beauty and skin care
have no gender.
How do you think my husband
stays so handsome and hot?
Baby, baby, uh, you know what?
This isn't the time.
We're talking about
a super urgent work matter.
Go and turn on the Jacuzzi, okay? Please.
Of course, babe.
Good evening, Mr. Lázaro.
Give my greetings to Claudia.
I'll let her know, Angélica.
- Good night.
- [Angélica] Thanks.
[sighs]
So, now we're ready to negotiate,
right, asshole? Come on, sit down.
THE KING OF THE MACHOS
[Estela] Charly!
What's up, Mom?
Ramón!
- What's going on?
- [laughs]
- Hey, bro. You look better in person, eh?
- [chuckles]
And how about that haircut?
Well, what did you think?
Well, to be totally honest,
I thought you'd look sort of nasty,
like a cross between a scarecrow
and ranch Goth.
- Ah, tell me how you really feel, eh?
- Uh-huh. You tell me.
[laughing]
No, but what are you doing here?
Well, what do you think?
I came to support you.
I wouldn't miss the final stretch
of the contest for anything in the world.
[chuckles] Hella awesome, bro.
I love you.
That's how I wanted to see you. Here.
Oh, wow.
Thanks.
Thanks, Mom, but why don't you
have one with us, eh?
No. It's early. Mmm.
I get buzzed very quickly. [chuckles]
[sniffs, whispers] Oh, my boys.
Come on, León! Beat that asshole!
Come on, man! Come on!
Let's go, man!
Keep going, you look like a fag!
- Let's go! Let's go, León!
- [grunting]
You've got it. Good.
It's a tractor, asshole. Let's go, pull!
Yair. Let's go. Good, man.
Good.
Damn right, man.
That butch will remember you.
I'm sure that she won't have a chance
in hell of beating you.
- [Charly] Cheers.
- [Ramón] Cheers, man.
Man, you're going to love the city.
You'll see.
There are a ton of places to visit.
Oh, I know. I'm pretty sure that
as soon as the busy season is over,
I'm heading there.
Well, I'm going to give you
a damn good tour.
You're not going
to want to come back here.
Well, maybe I'll just stay there, eh?
With the scholarship I'm getting
from the mayor,
I'm sure that I can go and study there.
- Wow, you've turned out cocky.
- Mm-hmm.
Well, cheers to that.
- Cheers.
- And more cheers.
Boys, I need your help. Come, please.
- What's wrong?
- I'll explain in a minute, just come.
This is a mistake.
We're an honorable family, Inspector.
This is an outrage.
Please, you can't do this to us.
Why are you shutting us down?
Someone reported an infestation.
Yes, and under the state health
and safety laws, we must close the hostel,
obviously, until an official inspection
can take place.
- My hostel is impeccable.
- There's no infestation here.
Well, we'll verify that
during the inspection.
For now, you must close your facilities,
and nobody can enter the property
until the experts come and inspect.
Are we clear on that?
But what about my guests?
I don't know, ma'am. Relocate them.
How are we going to relocate
so many tourists?
That's not my problem.
I'm just informing you.
But don't worry,
we'll try to resolve this quickly.
I'm sure it will be sorted out
in a few months.
And why don't you tell us who sent you?
Hmm? Aren't you the bootlicker
of Mr. Castillo, you sellout witch?
- No. Uh, Charly.
- Calm down.
Bring me to your boss.
We're going to settle this right now.
Any complaints can be filed
at the town attorney's office.
No, Inspector, give us a chance.
Can't you come and inspect right now?
- Put the stickers up, now.
- [Alonso] No, no.
Just wait a little, please.
Inspector, worker to worker,
I'm begging you. My hostel is impeccable.
I clean it myself,
there aren't any mosquitos.
Well, go and clean it, ma'am.
- [Estela] Don't talk to me like that, eh?
- Fucking witch.
What the hell, dude?
How you spoke pissed her off.
What can she do, huh?
Now she really won't want to help us.
Oh, don't bullshit me.
She wasn't going to help us, dude.
- Don't you see that Castillo sent her?
- Hey, tone it down, asshole.
We won't settle anything like that.
You're sounding like...
Like the town machos, right?
- You aren't like that.
- So, what am I like, Ramón?
I'd better go and get this shit solved.
See you later.
Hi, Charly, how are you?
How can I help you?
Yes, I need to see Jerónimo.
Unfortunately,
the mayor is not available today.
Don't worry, he understands.
Cha...
This gets rid of your baggy eyes.
How do you think my mom
looks like a ten and she's how old?
- But this isn't... Sir, this isn't my thing.
- Jerónimo.
- Charly.
- Charly. Ooh. What a surprise, eh?
Honestly, right now we're super busy.
We can't see you.
Yes. I'm sorry.
But they've just shut down the hostel
for no reason.
You know that our hostel is first-class.
I need your help to revoke the order.
I know that the Castillo family
has something to do with this.
[laughs] Charly, look. Honestly, as much
as I'd love to help you,
my hands are tied in this instance.
It's outside my jurisdiction.
Powers, sir.
- That.
- But if you can't help us, who can?
Uh, Juanito,
I think this is getting a little awkward.
Why don't you walk him to the exit,
and you give him one of the...
Contributions.
Contributions, uh-huh,
so that he leaves nice and happy.
No, Jerónimo, you know I wouldn't ask
you for anything if I didn't nee...
It was great to see you, eh? [chuckles]
Charly, Charly, forget it, come with me.
Come with me, Charly.
Thank you very much, eh?
Really, thanks for coming by.
Everything will be okay, Charly.
Gentlemen, shut the doors.
Juanito, I need your help.
- [sighs]
- [Juanito chuckles]
Are you okay? Are you sure
you know what you're doing, Mr. Mayor?
Distancing yourself from Charly right now
will get you fried, politically.
Especially now that you're rising
in the polls
and the press in the capital
is speaking very highly of you.
Johnny, drop it.
We have to move past this,
because the truth is,
if Castillo publicizes everything
he has on me,
I won't just take a beating in the polls,
it's going to be a knockout, eh?
And remember, just like with the Titanic,
if I sink, we all sink, bro.
[footsteps depart]
Just like with the Titanic.
[vendor speaking indistinctly]
- Hey, go Charly.
- You can do it, Charly.
[both chanting]
Charly, Charly! Charly, Charly!
[vendor continues]
THE KING OF THE MACHOS
THE EXTREME MACHO
PROTECT YOUR CHILDREN
FROM TRANS-GRESSIONS
One family. Two adults, two children.
- Come on in.
- Of course, of course. And a couple too.
- Thanks.
- Yes.
Mom. They need a room, too.
Have them go into the dining room, please.
I'll be with them soon.
Please have a seat, eh?
We'll be with you in a moment.
Oh, son.
Were you able to speak to the mayor?
- [Estela] What time would be good...
- What's up with Charly?
[sighs] I don't know, son.
He's been like that for days, like,
I don't even recognize him.
And it's awful that they've shut down
our hostel during this busy season,
but what breaks my heart the most
is seeing your mom so sad
because of your brother's behavior.
THE KING OF THE MACHOS
Remember to focus all your effort
in the chest and the abdomen,
not in the legs,
because you're going to slip.
And when you're there, you give it all
you've got in a single pull.
Hey, hey, I'm talking to you, dude.
- I'm paying attention, asshole.
- No, it doesn't look like it.
Ever since the mountain test
you've been acting weird, dude.
Come on, stop bullshitting me.
Okay, what do I have to do?
Once again. You have to focus
all your strength in the chest
and the abdomen.
If you focus on your legs,
you're going to slip.
If you put it there, you'll fall,
the weight will get the better of you.
Since no true macho is respected
without brute strength,
the next test is the tractor pull.
THE TRACTOR TEST
The contestants have only 90 seconds
to move a two-ton tractor
as far as possible.
The same one that the winner
of the grand finale
will be able to take home.
Well, boys, puff out those chests
and show us what you've got, ay ay ay!
[crowd cheering]
Abi, where are you? Why didn't you come?
It's time, my dear residents of Tunas,
for this test to begin!
Giddy up, boys! Start the clock!
THE TRACTOR
WHO IS THE MOST MACHO?
[contestant] It's not moving at all, dude.
[crowd booing]
[grunting]
Come on, León, you can do it!
Come on, asshole, you can do it!
[crowd chanting] León, León, León, León!
That's it! That's it!
[chanting continues]
[crowd cheering]
- Good. Good, son. Good.
- Good! Good, León!
That's enough.
[crowd member] Bravo!
[chanting] Charly, Charly, Charly, Charly!
Come on, what the hell?
So, she's really happy.
And they won't do anything?
Take care. See you later, Mr. Castillo.
How are you? A pleasure.
Excuse me, dear Charly.
Can you explain
what the hell you're doing?
The test consisted of moving
the tractor and I moved it.
That's bullshit!
Tha... That doesn't count, eh?
No, don't fuck with me. Don't bullshit me.
Of course! That's fucking unacceptable!
Men and women of Tunas.
What we've just witnessed
is unprecedented,
but there's nothing in the rule book
that specifies how the tractor
should be moved.
Mr. Mayor, please!
Someone has to bring order here!
Just a minute, calm down.
Calm down, dear residents of Tunas.
Being aggressive
has never gotten us anywhere.
While it's true that Charly moved
the tractor in an unconventional way,
Dr. Joel also said that nothing
in the rules forbids it.
So then, what would Pontius Pilate do?
[clears throat]
I proclaim this test eliminated.
I don't think that's fair at all! At all!
[announcer] This honorable council agrees
with this Solomonic decision.
The tractor contest
is officially eliminated.
Therefore, the contestants
must duke it out
in an emergency test
that will be announced
after we take a little break
because this has just been too much.
Therefore,
we'll be back soon with the finale.
Why would you eliminate the test, asshole?
Why the hell
didn't you eliminate the butch?
You keep protecting her
and you'll find yourself in jail
for being a dirty old man.
Do you know what they do
to men like you in jail?
You don't know, right?
[crowd chanting] León, León, León!
[crowd chanting] Charly, Charly, Charly!
Dear residents of Tunas,
the judges in charge of this contest
have decided that, for the emergency test,
the contestants must show their skill
to hang on and secure themselves
in one of the toughest tests...
THE MECHANICAL BULL TEST
...the mechanical bull.
The four contestants who fall
to the ground the fastest
will be immediately disqualified.
The other two will go directly
into the final round
of the King of the Machos.
Let the test begin.
[crowd] One, two three...
Two, three, four...
- [alarm buzzes]
- [announcer] Ah, no way!
Four, five, six, seven, eight, nine...
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight...
[announcer] Oh, so sad!
[phone pings]
[crowd chants] León, León, León!
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten, eleven!
- Good.
- Good, León! Good!
[Abigail]
On the bull, stay loose and go with it.
Your torso like a waving flag
and your hips
like you're caressing the bull.
[crowd] Two, three, four, five,
- six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven!
- Fall already.
[announcer] Oh, no, no. This kid's
putting up some real competition, eh?
And, let's see. Uh... Ah...
Silence, please.
We have the results here for...
Oh, what a grand finale.
What a grand finale.
With only 11 seconds, León Castillo
and Charly Tejeda are tied.
We have the final. Castillo versus Tejeda.
David versus Goliath.
You've got the green light.
Hey, and show no mercy.
Hey, Charly, my man.
Hey, dude, you rocked
that mechanical bull, eh?
Thanks.
Come on, get in. Want a few beers or what?
Sure.
Hell yeah, come on.
The thing about the mechanical bull
is that you have to be relaxed.
Because if your body is too tense,
then it won't work.
Yeah, dude.
I'd tell you that that's interesting,
but to be honest,
I don't give a fuck, asshole.
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong is that you're going
directly to hell, asshole.
The game's up for you.
Let's see if you finally fucking realize
that you make us all sick.
You're going to drop out of the contest,
you hear me?
And what if I don't?
This is what will happen to you,
fucking Charlota. [grunts]
[Charly grunting]
[grunting continues]
Are we clear? And one more thing.
If we see you near Abigail again,
you're dead, asshole.
Let's go.
- Eat, Dad.
- This is great, Mom.
- Made with lots of love.
- We know, sweetie.
[Ramón] Charly.
My God, Charly.
- What happened to you?
- What did they do to my son? [cries]
What did they do to you? Who was it?
God.
Let's see.
All done.
To top it all off, I fucked up with Toña.
And I only cause problems for all of you.
- No.
It's my fault they shut down the hostel.
Look, the hostel thing
will get sorted out sooner or later.
And well, bro, you knew what
you were getting into
when you signed up for the contest.
Obviously, in a town like this...
Well, they weren't going
to just let you win so easily.
The worst part of it is...
is that you believed the whole thing
about who is the most macho.
Why?
Because two or three dudes
cheered for you?
Since when did you become like them?
You're not like that.
Look, bro,
we're always going to support you.
Yes.
Always.
But you have to keep being yourself.
I think that what's most important now,
with everything that's happened,
is for you to let go of your ego
and drop out of the competition.
[grunts]
No.
I can't do that.
If I drop out now,
I have no way to teach the people
how fucking toxic this contest is.
Mom. I'm sorry for behaving like an idiot.
No. It's done now.
Dad, you were right.
I should have listened to you.
Forgive me.
I...
I know that I messed up.
But please give me the chance
to make things right.
[cries]
Okay.
[vendor speaking indistinctly]
[Charly] ♪ A friend is a treasure
Not easy to find ♪
♪ True friends
Can be counted on one hand ♪
♪ On winter days
When I don't see the sun shine ♪
♪ You're by my side,
Silent and without judgment ♪
♪ When I need a shoulder
And to dry my tears ♪
♪ I always count on you
I'll never be alone ♪
♪ Forgive me for failing you
Forgive me for hurting you ♪
♪ Forget the pain
That won't let you forgive ♪
♪ Forget the past
And let's begin again ♪
♪ Forgive me for failing you
Forgive me for hurting you ♪
♪ Forgive me for failing you ♪
♪ Forgive me for hurting you ♪
I'm sorry.
Truly.
I really fucked up with you, Antonia.
You don't know how much I regret it.
And you still helped me. You were there.
Without your advice,
I would have fallen off
the mechanical bull within two seconds.
But you still kept acting
like an imbecile.
It's like you never learn, dude.
Then you started acting like a macho.
Look, honestly, you seemed pathetic.
I know. Forgive me.
But, well...
With that serenade,
and if you try a little harder,
you may find
that I've already forgiven you.
Really?
Oh! I hate being mad at you.
But I don't love that Charly.
I love the real one.
Not that Charly you turned into
to please everyone else.
I promise.
And I want to promise you
that I'll always be here for you.
You know, it just so happens
that my mom made enchiladas today.
- Wanna go eat?
- That sounds incredible.
But there's something I need to fix first.
You make me very happy.
Back atcha.
[Charly] Bye.
What the hell are you doing here?
Get lost.
Or what? Are you going to send
those assholes to beat me up again?
What? I don't know what the hell
you're talking about, asshole.
Oh, no? So then, you also don't know
what happened to the hostel, right?
I don't have anything
to do with that, dude.
Don't act stupid, León.
Look, idiot. Just so you know,
my dad found out about you and Abi
and he's beyond furious.
Knowing him, I'm sure it was him.
And be grateful you got off so easily,
asshole, because my sister didn't.
Why? Is she okay?
Stay away from her.
Just tell her that I came to see her.
That's it.
You and I will meet in the finale.
You have no fucking clue what's at stake
for me in this contest, asshole.
I need to win to get out
of this fucking town.
I understand
because I want the same thing.
And because I saw
what your dad does to you.
What the hell are you talking about?
That it's not okay that he beats you.
The one who should feel ashamed is him.
It's not your fault, León.
No. No, you're wrong.
I don't want anything to do with you.
[footsteps depart]