Mr. Mayor,
we keep dropping in the polls.
I told you that it was a very bad idea
to stop supporting Charly.
We've lost many points
from decided voters around the state.
[shushes] Look... [chuckles]
What's wrong, little one?
We said we weren't going to
talk about that anymore.
No need to cry over spilled honey.
Cry over spilled milk, sir.
And please, you need to
start supporting that kid again.
That's not possible, that's not possible.
But, you know what? What I do need
is for all of the assistants...
I don't know, give them, uh,
a plot of land, a little truck,
but please, make sure
they're all happy and quiet.
- [laughs]
- Why?
[scoffs]
Why?
THE KING OF THE MACHOS
- Toma de referee. Good.
- [Charly whispers] Legs.
- [Ramón] Legs planted. Legs planted.
- [Charly] Ah!
That's judo, you use your own elasticity
to break free from your opponent.
- Come here, I'll show you another one.
- Yeah.
You come here. This one's very simple.
Grab your opponent's arm,
you turn, and you're in control.
Ah, let go! I... I got it.
This is useless.
I'm much weaker than León.
You think that I can get him
into a hold like this? There's no way.
Well, yeah.
Maybe León is stronger than you,
but you're faster, bro.
That makes you unpredictable.
- You have to change your attitude now. Eh?
- [sighs] Yeah.
I mean, you can't go into the ring
like that, all defeated.
Obviously you'll lose.
Come on, show some attitude!
Good, good, good, good!
- Okay. Okay. Yeah.
- Come on, you try it. Ready?
- Like that. Like that. Like that.
- You've got it. That's it, that's it.
- Hell yeah, that's it.
- Yeah? Hey.
Look, when you're facing León
and he tries to pull,
you're going to use his own strength
against him to take control.
I'll explain. Come here.
Ready? Pull me, but pull me hard.
There you go. Enough.
And he can't get out, eh?
- Okay.
- Good. Try it.
Yeah.
- Face-to-face, eyes...
- Mm-hmm.
[phone ringing]
I have to take this.
Abi?
[lock clicks]
[chuckles]
[sighs]
Are you okay?
My parents found out about us.
Your dad hit you?
Let's just say that he's not
the only Castillo with a heavy hand.
Your mom?
[Abi] And from what I can tell,
it was no picnic for you either.
It was my dad who spoke
with Jacobo and those guys,
and with the mayor,
so they'd shut down your parents' hostel.
And I thought that León was
the one behind it.
No.
León lives with my dad's foot on his neck,
but he's not as rough as he seems.
Your brother is hiding
a lot of things, isn't he?
[chuckles]
What's wrong?
Abi, our relationship
has only brought you trouble.
I think it would be best to break it off.
No, no, Charly.
Is that really what you want?
[sighs]
Ah, I have something for you.
What I just gave you is a bomb,
and I don't know what will happen
to my family when it explodes.
My only hope is that León can escape
from all the bullshit my dad's
involved in, and from this town.
[bell tolls]
WELCOME TO THE BIG EVENT
THE KING OF THE MACHOS
[Inés] Today is, without a doubt,
the most important
and exciting day of the year.
The Cowboy Corral is filled with people
who've come from near and far
to witness the crowning
of our next Macho King.
It's an exciting day
here in San José de las Tunas,
perhaps the only one, in this town
where nothing ever happens.
Today, the contest to select
the winner of...
Look, there's your spot.
Come on.
- [Alonso] Good day.
- How are you? [chuckles]
- [Alonso] Welcome.
- How are you?
- I'll see you later, Grandpa.
- Good afternoon.
That way.
[Inés] Good luck, Charly.
Mr. Mayor, it's so good to see you here,
especially with how busy you are.
Look, I just wanted to thank you
for all your support.
You've helped me much more
than you realize, eh? [chuckles]
Charly.
Thanks.
I'm going for a bottle opener, eh?
Afternoon.
Do you have a bottle opener, please?
Yep, that's the one.
- Now...
- Good afternoon, sir.
Good afternoon, miss.
A pleasure. Pepe Tejeda.
My pleasure. Fidelia, but call me Fides.
What a musical name.
Fides, Fidelia, like the opera.
Oh, my, how did you know that's my name?
What's my name?
Ah, Pepe Tejeda. A pleasure.
Your servant and friend, eh?
Fidelia, my pleasure, but call me Fides.
- Fides, Fidelia.
- Mm-hmm.
Would you like a little drink?
Sure.
A glass for the little lady, please.
You're going to love this.
- It's all vitamins, you'll see.
- Thanks.
It keeps me looking great.
From the start, show her who's boss,
and go for broke with that fucking broad,
dude. No mercy.
- Ooh, ooh, ooh!
[friend] Good, dude.
You just focus
and use his attacks against him.
Remember, skill is better than strength.
And you've got more than enough,
little brother. [chuckles]
Hey, focus.
Let's go.
Hope you're having a very good afternoon,
dear residents of Tunas and visitors.
Today is a crucial and iconic day
for everyone.
The grand finale is about to start!
[cheering, whistling]
The great battle that
we've awaited for weeks:
the final duel between
Charly Tejeda and León Castillo.
Let the competitors come in!
And let's hear it for your macho.
THE FINAL TEST
MACHO DUEL
A brutal fight, hand-to-hand combat,
sweat-to-sweat.
[spectators cheering]
[chanting] Evil will not triumph,
evil will not triumph!
[chanting] Charly, Charly, Charly!
Fight tough! Finish her, my boy!
Bravo, son!
[Antonia] Tempers are running hot,
and you know why?
- Why?
Because people know that
we're about to make history!
- That's right! Go, Charly, go!
- Don't go anywhere, folks.
Attaboy!
LEÓN is the BEST!
- Go, Charly!
- [Joel] Round one!
[bell rings]
- [friend] Focus. Focus.
- [Ramón] Go, Charly! You've got this, bro.
Good!
[friend] Break him, asshole!
You've got it!
[Ramón] You've got him, don't let go!
Go, Charly! Good!
- He's back up! That's it!
- Go, Charly!
- [Ramón] There it is! That's it!
- [friend] León, pressure.
[friend speaks indistinctly]
You've got it, you've got it! There!
Squeeze her, squeeze her!
You've got it. Come on, León.
[Ramón] Nothing, nothing.
That's it!
You've got it.
She's tired, she's tired, León!
Now's the time! Let's go!
Great, León!
[both straining]
Underneath, underneath, dude!
[Ramón] Come on!
You've got it! There, you've got him.
- Hey.
- [Charly groans, yells]
- Hey, what about that stomp?
- [friend] Good, dude! Good!
That's it! Hell yeah, assholes.
That's it! Good.
[Joel]
And the winner of this round is León...
- Bravo!
- ...with a super hold.
- Good.
- [bell ringing]
- [horn blares]
- León Castillo!
- Let's go! [chuckles]
- León, León, León!
Come here. How are you feeling?
- Good.
- Really?
[Ramón sighs]
Charly, you have to focus.
You know what to do
if things get ugly. Mmm?
How are you feeling?
- I'm fine.
- Come on. Come on.
You can do this.
[Joel] Round two!
- [bell rings]
- Come on, Charly, it's your turn!
[referee] Round two.
- [Joel] León looks confident...
- [whistle blows]
...with the advantage he's carrying
from the first round.
[Ramón] Come on, Charly, come on, come on!
[Lázaro] And pay attention
to what you're doing!
[friend] There you go, León, good.
Tire her out, tire her out, León!
[Ramón] That's it,
don't give in, don't give in!
[friend] Squeeze tight, dude.
You have to squeeze.
Come on, León.
[Ramón] Good, do it again!
- [Antonia] Come on, Charly! You can do it!
- Charly, be strong!
[Ramón] Hey, it's okay.
Get up, get up, get up!
Stop toying with her and finish her off,
knock her down!
[Ramón] Focus! That'll work, there it is.
[friend] Pressure, pressure. Good!
No, no, no!
Get lower. Cover yourself.
- Here, squeeze the elbow!
- [groans]
[Ramón] Good! Come on.
Once more, once more.
Show me that you're not
as big a dumbass as you look, damn it!
- [friend] No, no, León!
- [Ramón] That's it!
[Charly yells]
- Fuck yeah!
- That's it!
- [bell ringing]
- [Marquito] Go, Charly!
- Good!
- [Estela cheers]
- [laughs]
- [Charly] That's it!
That's my granddaughter's boyfriend.
[Antonia] Go, Charly!
- [Estela] Let's go!
- Let's go, Charly!
- Charly Tejeda!
- [horn blares]
[Charly] Yeah!
Go, Charly!
[in English] Then back.
[in Spanish] We're not supporting
Charly anymore, eh?
- Why not?
- Shh. I'll tell you later.
- León, León, León!
- Charly, Charly, Charly!
León, León, León, León, León!
[Joel] We're seeing incredible things
in today's match.
The participant who wins this round
will be crowned for all eternity
as the machoest macho of all the machos
in San José de las Tunas.
[exclaims]
Round three!
- [bell rings]
- [Miriam] Come on!
If he doesn't win, I'll kill him.
Finish off Charlota, asshole.
Don't be fooled
by that witch's tricks, dude.
Ready to checkmate those Castillos?
Come on, dog.
Come on. Stay strong.
[referee] Fighters, to the ring.
Round three.
[whistle blows]
- [horn blares]
- Fight.
[Charly groaning]
[friend] You've got her,
you've got her! There!
[Charly strains]
[León groans]
[friend] Come on, León, focus.
[Lázaro] Finish her off, dumbass!
Come on, son!
[groaning, straining]
Good. Don't let him go. Don't let him go.
[grunting, straining continues]
[friend] Shit, come on!
[Lázaro] You're useless!
Get that lesbian off of you, fuck it!
[León yells, groans]
[Ramón] That's it, Charly, that's it.
Let's see if you grow some balls, asshole!
You look like a fucking fool!
Don't talk to him like that,
he's not doing so badly.
[Lázaro] You look like a little fag!
[spectators gasping]
[Antonia] Charly, you can do it!
- Stay strong, son! Stay strong, son!
- Let's go, Charly!
Attaboy, Charly!
[both straining]
[León yells, groans]
[Charly groans]
- [León] Hell yeah, assholes!
- [whistle blows]
[spectators cheering]
[Lázaro] Hell yeah!
Attaboy! Attaboy!
A Castillo never loses!
And the undisputed winner of
The King of the Machos is León Castillo!
[horn blares]
All that glitters is not gold.
Trust me, bro.
- [shouts]
- [spectators cheering]
[friend] Hell yeah!
[fireworks whistling, crackling]
[chanting] Charly, Charly, Charly,
Charly, Charly, Charly!
Charly, Charly, Charly, Charly, Charly,
Charly, Charly, Charly, Charly, Charly!
[spectators continue chanting]
My dears, as you can see,
the audience confirms it,
Charly is the undisputed winner
of this town!
Way to go, Charly!
- [spectators whistling, cheering]
- [Antonia] Go, Charly!
[spectators chanting] Charly, Charly,
Charly, Charly, Charly, Charly!
AUDIENCE OVATION FOR
CHARLY TEJEDA
AFTER SECOND-PLACE FINISH
[spectators] Charly, Charly!
- [Marquito] Way to go, champ!
- [Antonia] My dears...
[Víctor]
Dear residents of Tunas and visitors,
presenting the new King of the Machos,
León Castillo.
[triumphant music playing]
- [Joel] In your honor, in your honor.
- [Víctor chuckles]
León, I give you the biceps,
with the whole body,
a replica of your ancestor,
Mr. Anastasio Castillo,
may he rest in peace,
and not be offended by my words.
[Joel] He will be proud of you.
[Miriam] We also give you
this enormous check in cash
for 50,000 pesos.
FIRST-PLACE WINNER
And, last of all, we're giving you
the keys to this beautiful tractor,
which has been proven to be
an agricultural beast,
worthy of the most macho tasks.
[Víctor laughs]
[horns blaring]
[Joel] What is Mr. Lázaro doing here?
[Víctor] You can tell
he likes the spotlight.
[Joel chuckles] Yeah.
[Joel laughs]
Uh, welcome, Lázaro.
A round of applause.
Generations of machos. [chuckles]
Today, we're all winners,
except for Charly,
who ended up in second place.
- Come and get your certificate, please.
- [Miriam chuckles]
THE KING OF THE MACHOS
SECOND PLACE
[chuckles] Here it is, eh?
- Congratulations. Congratulations.
- Bravo!
[Miriam] This has been a great edition,
dear men and women of Tunas.
[Víctor] Ah, it was thrilling.
Right, Mr. Joel?
Abigail - You saved my brother
Now... Save us all!!
[Joel] They've raised the bar very high.
Miriam?
[Miriam laughs]
We'll see you in the next edition of
- The King of the Machos.
- [Joel, Víctor] The King of the Machos.
[Joel speaks indistinctly] No, no. No, no.
There it is. Mr. Victor, Mr. Victor.
Oh... [speaks indistinctly]
[mic feedback echoes]
Honestly, I've had to walk
a very difficult path
that has been full of obstacles.
And not just me.
Even my family has been attacked
by the closure of our hostel,
an unjustified and arbitrary action
that was planned by Mr. Lázaro Castillo.
[spectators gasping]
One thing I can say for sure
is that we all know
that Mr. Lázaro Castillo
has been controlling the town
with threats and intimidation for years.
What you don't know is that he also
treated himself to buying the elections
so that Navarro would be in power.
And if you don't believe me,
here is the proof.
[all gasping]
FROM L. CASTILLO - $1,475,000
FROM L. CASTILLO - $4,000,000
FROM L. CASTILLO - $7,400,000
And why do you think Castillo would spend
so much money for something like this?
It's so he can boss the mayor around
however he wants,
so that the government
will support his businesses,
- leaving all of us in second place.
- That's photoshopped,
and what's coming out of her mouth
are pure lies, it's slander.
- Those are donations. Yes, I'm sure.
- Donations.
Come on, please, take the microphone away
from that butch now.
Are you finished, Lázaro?
No, I'm not finished with you,
fucking bitch!
I'm going to sue you
until you have to pawn your last tooth.
- Get out of here! Get out of here!
- [Lázaro] Claudia, León.
- Get out!
- Out!
- Pig!
- [Lázaro] Claudia! Claudia!
[Charly] But I'm not finished.
[camera shutter clicks]
Do you remember when I was
the mayor's favorite pet?
- [Jerónimo] No, don't start with all that.
- [Angélica] No, Juanito, enough.
How do you think Castillo managed to
get him to turn his back on me
and order the hostel to be shut down?
Hey, hey, hey! Look, look.
Charly, that's unrelated, eh?
That stuff is pure fake news. [chuckles]
Don't waste spit denying it, Jerónimo.
I have proof. I have proof.
But I'll warn you
that this is sensitive stuff.
[Jerónimo stammers]
So, what... Proof of... I think that...
[spectators gasping]
[Angélica] What the hell, Jerónimo?
What the hell, Jerónimo?
- What the fuck is this? What the hell!
- [stammers] No...
And on top of that, you bring me to live
in this fucking town full of scumbags!
I hate you all!
I hate San José de las Tunas!
[spectators booing]
[Angélica] Move!
Get lost, leave! Leave! Leave! Leave!
[all] Leave! Leave! Leave! Leave!
[chanting] Leave! Leave! Leave! Leave!
Leave! Leave! Leave! Leave!
Bye! Good luck with your campaign!
[spectators chanting]
Leave, leave, leave, leave!
[Charly] In the beginning,
I entered this contest
to prove that I could be
as manly as anyone in this town,
but that's not necessary anymore.
This whole deal, that in this town
a man doesn't count if he isn't macho,
if he doesn't just take it
when he's in pain,
if he doesn't treat women badly.
All that and for what?
That's why, although it's up to you,
I say that this contest
should disappear forever.
[spectators cheer]
As for me, I know
what kind of man I am and want to be,
and I don't have to prove it to anybody.
Down with The King of the Machos!
[chanting]
No! No, no, no, no. Of course not!
- Down with The King of the Machos!
- [Eduviges] Of course not!
Down with The King of the Machos!
WE STAND WITH CHARLY
[chanting]
Down with The King of the Machos!
Dear viewers, I'm Inés Montoya,
and what we're witnessing today is
a watershed moment
in San José de las Tunas.
Our town has never experienced
a revolution of this magnitude.
THE KING OF THE MACHOS
EDITION CXVI - YEAR 2022
But what am I seeing?
Machorrín?
Down with The King of the Machos!
[chanting]
Son! Very good! Good!
- [Alonso] We won, son!
- Down with The King of the Machos!
SAN JOSÉ DE LAS TUNAS REBELS
AGAINST THE KING OF THE MACHOS
This is certainly a town
that we can be proud of.
Down with The King of the Machos!
Down with machos!
Shut up.
Okay, okay, okay. Hey, excuse me.
Okay, okay. Okay.
Honestly, I can't believe...
What are you saying, woman?
Down with The King of the Machos!
If it weren't for your shenanigans,
I'd never see you.
[chanting continues]
You know me, I can't stay still.
- [laughs]
- [Angélica] Come here, Jerónimo!
- Great, scoundrel, eh?
- Hi, Toñito.
- Lázaro! Lázaro, Lázaro.
- Let's grab some beers
- and tell me what you're up to.
- Dude, wait.
Like, what's up
with what's going down here?
Lázaro, my ass!
If you'd stopped that witch
at the right time,
we wouldn't be in this mess now.
So now you go
and get yourself out of it, dumbass.
- [Jerónimo mumbles indistinctly]
- Claudia.
[Jerónimo chuckles] Psst.
- [Lázaro] Take care of them. Let's go.
- But... Uh, but... Claudia...
- The family, dude.
- How dare you, Jerónimo?
- Don't hit me again, eh?
- Fucking corn-face!
That's what you learned
from your cheap soap operas, eh?
You've cost me too much,
you've cost me too much!
CHANGING ROOM MEN
[water running]
[León] Why did you let me beat you?
I didn't let you beat me.
Don't bullshit me,
I know perfectly well what you did.
Who cares?
León, you can leave this town.
Your dad will never lay
another finger on you.
What's this?
They're the keys to the tractor,
it's half of the prize.
It's only fair, Charly.
Thanks.
[bell tolls]
[student]
At 7:00 in the multipurpose room,
we'll have a discussion
about sexual diversity.
You're all invited.
Come on out, at 7:00. Don't miss it.
Oh, Doloritas, my comadre,
what a disgrace our town has become!
Oh, my comadre, with so much revolution,
honestly, I've realized a few things
and I have to tell you something.
[Pepe] I'd like you to meet Charly,
he's my grandson
and we're very proud of him.
Nice to meet you, son. Congratulations.
[chuckles] Nice to meet you, ma'am.
Thanks, Grandpa.
[sighs]
Never come down from the clouds, okay?
We'll miss you.
And I'll miss you, dear Marquito.
[chuckles]
[both chuckle]
Wow, it's so hot, isn't it? [sniffles]
- Even my eyes are sweating.
- [chuckles]
SAN JOSÉ DE LAS TUNAS
BUS STATION
It's okay.
[Charly sniffles]
You sure you won't come with me?
With the sale of the tractor,
we can see what happens, or not.
No, no, no, I don't know, just wait.
I need my time.
Besides, you and I will always be together
in some way or another. Right?
Or did you think
you could get rid of me so easily?
[chuckles, sniffles] I know I can't.
No.
[Charly sobs]
I love you, Antonia.
Love you too.
With my whole heart.
Are you sure you have to go, son?
Yes, Mom.
I'm going to miss you a ton.
But I can't stay in this town.
[Alonso] Remember that
whenever you need us, we'll be here.
You know that I couldn't have
done it without you, right?
[Charly cries]
- [laughs]
- [Estela chuckles]
[Charly] It looks like me.
[chuckles]
[bus engine starts]
- Bye, Charly.
- [Charly chuckles] Bye.
[Estela] Bye.
[Pepe] Attaboy, Charly.
[door closes]
Translated by Catharine Lailson