Whew.
- BoJack?
- I'm back in L.A.
- I should have called you...
- Yeah. You should have.
- I said I was sorry.
- No, you didn't.
- Okay. Good to hear from you, BoJack.
- No...
Ugh.
What the...?
Okay, thank you.
What's going on here?
Fundraising dinner for the
Peanutbutter for California campaign.
- All right, I'm just gonna...
- Sorry. It's a fundraiser.
- Uh...
- BoJack!
I love your ironic take
on black-tie attire.
It really says, "I truly don't
care what you think of me."
This light bulb won't let me in
to your house without paying.
Ah, sorry about that.
Gotta raise those funds.
- Can't I just...
- Thanks for your support, buddy.
- Means so much. Erica!
- Hey...
Look at you, with the
right number of ears!
- Look, I just...
- Twenty thousand dollars a plate.
Hmm...!
Oh.
Hey, do you have another bathroom?
They're all occupied, and I gotta pee.
Not because I'm pregnant or anything.
Because if I were pregnant, it would
be bad luck to tell you this early.
Presuming it was early.
But I'm not pregnant.
This is just a normal, non-pregnant
gal type of having to pee.
- There's a bathroom in the pool house.
- You're a lifesaver.
Pardon me! Out of my way.
Uh-oh. Am I in Ithaca?
Because you are looking
"gorges" this evening.
Well, I must be in Nazi Germany,
because you're "not so" bad yourself.
- I'm sorry, yours was better.
- Hi.
Whoa.
Well, I should go.
Looks like the work wife/ex-wife
is talking to my other ex-wife.
- You have two ex-wives here?
- Katrina's his campaign manager.
And Jessica Biel loves
getting photographed
at fancy fundraisers.
If it isn't my two favorite ladies,
in the same room! This is great.
- Hey.
- BoJack, I'm busy.
You haven't seen me for
a year and a half.
Yeah, because you disapp...
No, I am not doing this now.
- Why don't you get yourself a drink?
- I will get a drink.
I will get $20,000 worth of drinks.
Oh, Norman, we have to support the...
- Ooh, yes.
- All right.
Hi, Zach Braff. Zach Braff.
Hey there. Famous actor
Zach Braff, how you doing?
Everyone?
Thank you all for being here.
We're gonna beat that scoundrel
Woodchuck Coodchuck-Berkowitz...
Boo!
...and bring likability
back to politics.
I especially want to thank my
pro-fracking pals for
being here tonight.
You know, my wife said, "Don't
frack," but we did it anyway,
and it all worked out.
- Love you, sweetie.
- Mm-hmm.
Finally... oh! Sorry about that, folks.
I sensed an earthquake.
Must have been a false...
Oh, hey now!
Nope, I was definitely wrong.
Listen to me, I'm the dog
who cried earthquake.
- We're gonna die!
- Oh, fudge!
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- I can't die!
I'm not famous enough yet to make the
"In Memoriam" montage at the Oscars!
I have so many regrets!
I just picked up a family sitcom
where the mom is a zombie!
It's called Mombie, and it's terrible!
I have a condition where every time
I sense a shift in power dynamics,
I have a tiny orgasm!
I have no original ideas, I
just repeat things I hear.
- I've never been in love!
I tried gay at theater camp!
I regret everything!
Whoa!
synced & corrected by PopcornAWH
www.addic7ed.com.
Hello?
Is anyone getting any bars?
I'm not getting any baa-rs.
Can someone validate my valet ticket?
I would like to go home now.
There's no way out. Okay.
Everybody stay sane.
I propose we set each
other on fire for warmth.
Who wants to be set on fire first?
Not me, I'm Jessica Biel.
Yeah, that's right.
The natives are getting restless,
so why don't you say
something to comfort them?
Okay. Everyone, remain calm!
No one's going to light anyone on fire.
For one thing, that'd
eat up a lot of oxygen
and who knows how much
we have down here.
- I want oxygen!
- Air! I need air!
God.
- You okay, sweetie?
- I think so.
- That was really scary.
- Yeah.
At least we know no one
is specifically at fault.
Well, except for San Andreas.
This was because you
fracked under our house.
I told you fracking was
dangerous, and you didn't listen.
And now our house is ruined and
we're trapped underground,
and we're all going to die!
- Is this one of our sexy fights?
- No!
Hmm.
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
You can be mad at me or get drunk
with me, but you can't do both.
Watch me.
Oh, what the shit?
- Oh, fish.
- Uh... hello?
- What are you doing in there?
- Uh, I live here.
Didn't you know there was
a huge party going on?
I was going to go to the
party after my bath,
but then I realized the
bath was the party.
Oh, God.
Well, I'm not waiting around
to be rescued like some chump.
Come on, let's go.
Whoa...!
- We gotta go in there?
- Well, I don't see any other way.
Sometimes life is like the second
season of Friday Night Lights...
You gotta push through and hope
there's better stuff ahead.
Aw-ww!
Guys, let's all try to just stay cool
and make the best of things, huh?
"Make the best of things"? You idiot,
we're trapped and we're terrified.
Okay, settle down, you future
hard Jeopardy question.
Let's hear what the idiot has to say.
So that's a re-up on the idiot part?
How are we supposed to
make the best of things?
- We're stuck underground.
- This is true.
But most of us are
important celebrities,
so someone will come for us soon.
And for you regulars, I'm sure
they'll bring you up with us!
What do we do till then?
We're actors! I say we put on a show.
Who's with me?
A show? Who will be the star?
Me, I assume.
Sure you'll be the star,
and you'll be the star!
And you'll be the star!
We'll all be the star!
Folks, I promise you we will
be out of here in no time.
And that's when I realized...
I just don't have the face for bangs.
Oh, my God, thank you so much.
You're too kind! Thank you.
Thank you, Phoebe, for that rousing
Tale from the Above Ground. Who's next?
I can't take this anymore.
I need to get out.
This is the longest I've
gone without moisturizing,
- and I feel like a lizard!
- Humph.
- No offense.
- It's only been 72 hours.
I'm missing my general meeting at CBS.
I'm supposed to get baa-ck to work.
I can't live like this! We've
gotta light someone on fire.
I'm starting to think that less-famous
Michelle Monaghan has the right idea
- about lighting people on fire.
- Thank you.
Come on, party people, keep it together.
Let's not forget why we're here...
To raise money for my campaign,
and more recently, to not go
crazy and murder each other.
Can someone please bring me my car?
It's a Prius. A silver Prius.
You're killing me, Zach.
Mr. Peanutbutter, you can do this.
Be the leader that I know you can be.
Yeah. You're right.
I've totally got this.
What in the world?
"Vox clamantis in deserto."
- It is I.
- Woodchuck Coodchuck-Berkowitz!
- We're saved!
- Wow!
Oh, thank God. A leader.
Sh.
What's going on down here?
Anyone's looking for us?
We're cool. Just being
cool, don't worry.
Diane, have you just been getting
drunk with BoJack this whole time?
What? I'm still mad at you.
- Citizens, remain calm.
- Yeah, that's what I've been saying!
Rescue workers are coming
but it could be a while.
State emergency funds have been
depleted due to budget overruns
on a costly bridge to Hawaii
that's being constructed.
Oh, yeah!
Since a woodchuck is a digging
animal, I came to get you out early.
Is that what a woodchuck is? Why
did I think it was like a beaver?
What's it like out there, Woodchuck?
Whole neighborhood totaled?
- Is the city in chaos?
- No, it's really just your house.
Because of all the fracking that's
been happening underneath your house.
Oh! Interesting!
- Ay-yi-yi.
- Oh, right, right.
So you just burrowed down here to rescue
your political opponent's top donors.
That's convenient.
It was actually very inconvenient,
but I put politics aside to
save you people from dying.
Three cheers for Woodchuck!
Hip, hip, hooray!
Please, don't cheer too loudly.
The tunnel is very delicate.
- Hip, hip, hooray!
- Seriously, I think it's best to...
Hip, hip, hooray!
- Let's cheer one more time,
- just for fun!
- No, please.
- Four cheers. Why not? Hip, hip...
- Hooray!
No!
So turns out three cheers was probably
an adequate number of cheers.
- What was that?
- Just keep walking.
God, I can't wait to get home.
I don't even have a home anymore.
Oh, man, where am I going to keep all
my different colored hats I never wear?
Well, if you need another couch to
crash on, there's always my place.
- Didn't you move in with Ralph?
- Yeah, but I kept the old apartment.
- Just in case, I guess.
- In case of what?
What was that?
Whoa!
Oh!
Now, ladies, just calm down.
We can talk about this.
What are we gonna do, Princess Carolyn?
Did you say you're a princess?
- That's just my name. I'm a manager.
- It's like an agent.
- It's totally different.
- Is it, though?
- Silence! You negotiate deals?
- Mm-hmm.
You could be of service,
Manager Carolyn.
My hands... they're crushed.
There's no way I can
dig us back out now.
Well, I can dig!
Actually, no one should dig.
Your foundation is
basically Swiss cheese.
The slightest provocation,
could cause another collapse
that would crush us all.
I know that because I bought a sitcom
about fracking, The Frack Shack.
It's New Girl meets fracking.
Oh, God, no one's gonna
watch that show, huh?
Someone will be coming for us soon.
In the meantime, we must organize.
Parcel out food and water
and see how much we've got.
- I'll assign team leaders.
- Oh, no. I'm sensing a shift in power.
All right. Um...
- God...!
- For you, a banana
- because you're so appealing.
- Yeah.
And for you, a radish. Enjoy.
Mr. Peanutbutter, this is a disaster.
I don't think so. I'm food
captain, and I am loving it.
- And who made you the food captain?
- Woodchuck.
Exactly. He's in charge.
Excuse me, you have not been
allocated those rations.
I'm a horse. I need more
food, and I'm a celebrity.
- Everyone down here is a celebrity.
- Not the caterers.
Relinquish the food.
Hey. Here's your chance.
Actually, Woodchuck, this is my house
and BoJack can eat whatever he wants.
This man has already reached his
allotted food portion for the day.
Who said we have to go by your rules?
Yeah, who made you
leader of underground?
I'm just gonna take all this and...
You've appointed me. Yes, I under...
citizens, look...
Keep it together.
Weird stuff going on downstairs.
Humph.
- I can't believe this is my life.
- Uh-oh.
Too much sad booze for you.
Where's the happy booze?
I'm trapped underground and
it's all my husband's fault
and I'm gonna die in this mansion
in a mass grave with his ex-wives.
Okay. But on the bright side...
Look, Mr. Peanutbutter loves you, you
got a cool job, you got friends.
Jesus, you're right.
Even when I was above
ground, I wasn't satisfied.
Oh, my God. I'm the problem!
Whoa!
What the...?
Why can't I be happy? Am I busted?
No. It...
I am! I'm a pit.
I'm a pit that good things fall into!
Diane, you're not a pit.
I'm a pit!
I can't believe I'm crying.
This is so dumb.
It's okay. Don't feel
bad about feeling bad.
You disappeared for a year and a half.
So you do want to talk about it. Just
took four solid days of drinking.
If you were back in L.A.,
why didn't you call me?
- I wasn't... ready.
- Ready? For what?
I wanted to be better
when you saw me again.
And I thought I could be, somehow.
But I'm not.
And even if I did get better,
the best I could ever be
is still just some other version of me.
BoJack, I can't wait
for you to be better.
I need you in my life.
- Really?
- You're the biggest asshole I know,
and you're the only thing
that makes sense to me.
People should be able to have some
control over their lives down here.
- Yeah!
- People need boundaries.
Leadership means sometimes
being the bad guy.
You hear that? Woodchuck's a bad guy!
I don't want a bad guy to be our leader.
- That's not...
- That's a point for Mr. Peanutbutter.
And I'm the good guy, so
that's two points for me.
What points? There are no points.
- This is not a game!
- Well, maybe there should be points.
- Yeah!
- Points!
People seem to like my points idea.
That's another point for me.
Well, I'm the one who came down here
to save you in the first place.
Surely I get points for that.
Asking for points is conceited.
That's more points for me.
- He's right!
- What?!
If you came down to save
us, why are we still here?
Yeah!
You had one job, and you couldn't do it!
- Yeah!
- That's right.
Minus point for Woodchuck.
I implore you not to fall
into a mob mentality.
- He called us a mob! Let's kill him!
- Yeah!
Folks, Woodchuck's political
philosophy is as broken as his hands.
That is a convincing argument.
He does have broken hands.
Maybe it's time an
outsider took control.
An outsider like me, the
guy whose house this is.
Peanutbutter, Peanutbutter.
Peanutbutter... everybody.
Peanutbutter! Peanutbutter!
Peanutbutter!
- Me!
- Peanutbutter!
Peanutbutter! Peanutbutter...
BoJack. BoJack.
- BoJack.
- What?
- Did you know I can juggle?
- Cool.
Are you okay? I mean, outside
of our current situation
of being buried alive and
almost out of alcohol
except for cooking sherry and Midori?
It's just been a rough couple years
with Sarah Lynn dying and Herb.
- And Corduroy?
- Cordu-what now?
Corduroy? Jackson-Jackson? Died
of autoerotic "asphyx-ization"?
Oh, yeah, him too. And now I got this...
girl in my house, this... daughter-type.
You got daughter? Ruh-roh.
Yeah, I got daughter, "ruh-roh."
Supposed to help her figure
out who her mother is.
But I don't know where to start.
Did she try sending mutual consent
form to the adoption agency?
What, what words?
Well, if it's closed adoption,
you send a mutual consent form.
Basically says, "I wanna be open now!"
If Mom says same thing, boom-bah-boo!
Smo-pen Sesame!
- How do you know about that?
- I had an adopted brother.
And also for a while, I
hoped I was adopted.
- Ugh!
- Huh.
- Whoa!
- Ooh!
Who dares disturb Queen Antonia?
My name is Princess Carolyn.
I represent the soldiers
of Subcolony K-147,
who feel they're doing all the work
while reaping none of the spoils.
Everything my soldiers
do benefits the colony.
I had this same conversation
with Jeffrey Katzenberg.
Believe me, this doesn't
end well for you.
What are your demands?
They want to have sex with your drones.
My drones?
Mm-hmm.
Oliver, assemble the small council.
Uh, If we're gonna be down here
a while, can I get a new towel?
Woodchuck's aa-always
telling us what to do!
He says help is coming, but how
does he know? What if he's lying?
And I have still not been validated!
If you could all be patient...
We're sick of waiting! It's
time for new leadership.
That attempted movie star is right!
I declare Mr. Peanutbutter
President-for-life of Underground.
Yeah!
Uh, uh, oh!
- Thank you!
- What? No!
- What do we do with Woodchuck?
- He must be made an example of.
- Get him!
- Yeah!
All right, guys, all right. Calm down.
We don't need to "get him."
Let's just tie him up someplace
where he can't hurt us anymore
with his dangerous ideas.
Do not tie me up. That isn't necessary.
No, don't... no...!
- Peanutbutter!
- No!
- Thank you, thank you all.
As my first act as President-for-life,
I declare that everyone
is allowed to eat and
drink whatever they want!
Yeah!
Agh...!
I'm starving,
and not the normal celebrity kind
of starving like I always am.
Or even red-carpet-season starving.
- Where's the food?
- You ate all the food.
This is it!
Nobody's coming for us. We
need to kill someone for food.
- Hmm...!
- Oh...!
Let's eat Mr. Peanutbutter!
He has the word "peanut
butter" in his name!
Yeah!
Guys, guys, guys, maybe we
don't need to eat anybody!
What's this now?
Let's listen to the guy
who's saying don't kill me.
He's got some interesting ideas.
Listen to me, everyone. Please.
I'm known for monologues that sum
things up at the end of the show.
I drive a Prius, which
means I'm a good person.
Let's not surrender to
our basest instincts.
I know times are tough, but
I'm sure if we band together
and really concentrate
on the problem at hand,
we can, as a group of friends...
- Oh, my God.
- Biel!
The rule of man is over. Now
begins the rule of fire.
- Oh, why?
- Jessica, no.
I will no longer be shackled
by the civilized society
of the above ground.
This is Underground, and the
only law here is flame.
The fire wants not for justice.
The fire wants not for reason.
- The fire desires only to be fed!
- Feed the fire!
- The fire is my new god!
- Oh, God!
I'm so sorry, Mr. Peanutbutter,
but the tide has turned
and I side with the fire now.
Tonight, we dine on Zach Braff.
- Tomorrow, canine cuisine!
- No.
You, take him to his
spot, and make him stay.
No! No! Please!
Listen to reason... this time!
Ah-hh!
I think that's all of it.
I can't go back to my old life sober.
It's so empty.
Okay, okay. Here's the
secret to being happy.
Oh, I can't wait to hear this.
Just pretend you are happy,
and eventually you'll
forget you're pretending.
Maybe you're right.
I just need to stop
complaining and work harder.
Everyone else is doing it.
Why am I so special?
Lock him in here!
- Please! Diane, my sweet wife.
- What's going on?
Marvin Gaye.
The People of Underground
have a new god, the fire.
And for my crimes I will be
fed to its ravenous flames.
My only hope is the meat of
Zach Braff proves lasting,
but I fear by daybreak, there
will be no Braff meat left.
- What's going on?
- Four Non-Blondes.
Everybody out except the prisoner.
- No!
- Easy on the merchandise!
Get off me!
Well, it's been a tough week,
lots of back and forth,
but I think we've reached an agreement
that meets everybody's needs.
"The queen will share male sex
servants with the soldiers"
for one night of magnificent,
sensuous splendor,
a gorgeous bacchanal of
hedonistic delights,
"with a second orgy pickup option,
pursuant on success of the first."
My clients are satisfied
with those terms.
Great. Now can we please
return to the surface world?
All my favorite clouds are up there.
Oh, I like this one. He's got
moxie and a soft thorax.
How did you find your fleshy self in
my kingdom, you pink marshmallow?
We were at this big
Beverly Hills fundraiser.
There was an earthquake, and now
everyone's trapped underground.
Did you say Beverly Hills?
Ugh! Of course.
Surface dwellers are always
moving in on our territory.
First they move here, then taxes go up,
the next thing you know,
there's a Whole Foods.
How am I supposed to
concentrate on a great orgy
when I've got gentrification on my mind?
No, we've got to get those
interlopers out of here.
- Let's...
- Hey! Hold on.
- Uh...
- Mr. Peanutbutter,
did you or did you not tell us
we could eat whatever we wanted?
Peanutbutter!
Peanutbutter! Peanutbutter!
We gotta do something.
Mr. Peanutbutter's the only non-shitty
thing that's ever happened to me
and now they're gonna set him on fire.
Okay. What would non-hungover Diane do?
She's smart.
I don't know. I need water.
There is no more water.
That's the problem.
"Choodwuck" is right.
Wait, isn't there water, under
the ground? Like, a well?
- Yeah! And we're underground.
- If we dig, we'll get water!
Do not dig. The ground is very volatile.
Quiet, sky rodent! To the shovels!
Mr. Peanutbutter, your time is nigh.
Any last words before
we light you on fire?
Yes, if I could just say,
"Don't light me on fire"?
The fire bends to no man's will.
Nothing can defeat the fire. Only...
Water!
What?
- Oh, wow, it's really water.
- Water is stronger than fire.
Wait, let's not really
forget how... ugh!
Water is my new god now!
Oh, boy.
- Clear gold!
- All right, water!
H-2-Oh, boy, we hit
the freaking jackpot!
Hang on. It's... it's not stopping.
Which is great!
You hit a pipe, you drunken imbeciles.
H-2-Oh, no!
Well, I guess this is it.
Oh, God! It's another earthquake!
How is this happening?
Heave! Heave! Heave!
Get them out of here!
Okay.
No! Please! I'm important down here!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Oh, what an eyesore. The HOA
will be hearing about this.
We are never talking about any
of this ever again. Whew.
So I will see you tomorrow. We've
got a rally in Bakersfield
and then we're touring a tennis
ball factory in Modesto.
Okay.
- Hi.
You're the best thing
that ever happened to me.
- I don't tell you that enough.
- It's okay.
If this governor thing is
really important to you...
It's not. You saw me in there.
I'm a terrible leader.
I don't want to be governor. I
just wanted people to like me.
Well, I like you.
Come on, Diane, let's go home...
oh, right.
Well, thanks for inviting
me to your party.
I had a wonderful time.
Evening really flew by.
Sure.
- You guys hungry?
- I could eat.
Ethiopian?
Ooh, haven't done Ethiopian in a while.
I should go home. I haven't
seen my boyfriend in ten days.
He's probably worried about me.
I'm down for Ethiopian. I
love that sponge bread.
- What do they call it, "injera"?
- Yeah, injera.
- Injera, right.
- That's right.
Yeah, that's good bread.
synced & corrected by PopcornAWH
www.addic7ed.com.
Boxer vs. Raptor.