I mean, it's been a few decades.
All right, what was the proper etiquette
when they would... like,
would have sleepovers?
You mean, when they're hooking up?
- Yeah.
No nudity in shared spaces.
You seeing a little more of
the boyfriend than you care to?
So much more.
You need to set some boundaries.
I have, regularly.
And yet, I still got an eyeful
of Willy wonka this morning.
Where the hell are they going? Control,
7-Adam-15.
Advise status on any code
3 events near our location?
Negative, 7-Adam-15.
What was their hurry?
Let's find out.
Smitty, go to channel 9.
Go for smitty.
Where's your shop?
Where's my shop?
It's parked right out
wait a minute.
What's happening?
I've been waiting for you to wake up.
I think we should have a baby.
Is that something you're open to?
I'm... I... I... I don't know.
I love being a dad, but I think I thought
maybe my days of dirty
diapers and sleepless nights
were over.
But you were about to foster Anna.
No, yes.
That's true, I was.
But she had no one.
I think it kind of... it felt like fate.
So is that a no?
No, it's... it's an, "a I haven't even had"
"a cup of coffee yet.
Maybe we table this till later."
Absolutely.
This is a really big conversation,
so let's just think about it,
and we can talk again after work.
Right.
Ok.
Yeah?
On a scale of 1 to 10,
how stressed are you?
- 19.
- Yikes.
Tim still ghosting you?
He's not ghosting me.
We just haven't talked
in a couple of days.
Not speaking to the person you're dating
is the definition of ghosting.
I realize that.
Thank you.
So this probably isn't a good time to add
more stress to your plate.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's just I have a group
of friends at school,
and they're getting a place together,
and I was thinking of joining them.
You're moving?
Kind of.
- That's great.
- Really?
Yeah.
I mean, you should live
with people your own age.
I mean, I'll miss seeing you every day,
but if it makes you
happy, then that's great.
Good.
I was worried you'd be upset.
The house they picked is really cool.
I'll show you pictures after school.
I can't wait.
Hey.
Have you talked to Tim recently?
No.
I heard he was taking vacation days.
- Do you think he's in trouble?
- Yes.
I
He said that if he tells
me what he's doing,
I could put my career in jeopardy.
That's alarming.
I know.
Should I... should I tell grey?
No.
Hard as it is, you need to trust him.
Whatever he's doing, I'm
sure Tim's got it handled.
Ok.
So I'm just supposed to do
nothing, patrol like normal,
pretend like I'm not
worried out of my mind?
For now, yes.
Thanks.
And if you're just joining us
it's been a pitcher's clinic here,
tied ball game in the
bottom of the seventh, 2-all.
Hi.
My god.
What are you doing?
Being a friend.
Talk.
I can't.
For your own good.
Are you engaged in a criminal act?
Not at the moment.
Then tell me.
Angela, this goes sideways
and you're anywhere near it,
you could be fired.
If Lucy gets fired, it's a problem.
If I get fired, I start living
off my husband's trust fund
and call it wine o'clock.
So spill.
I'm tailing this guy from
my old unit, ray Watkins.
Spent his deployment
ripping off Iraqi locals,
got a couple of my men killed.
Till a few days ago, I thought he was kia.
Somehow he survived and now he's
living under a different
name as a hired gun.
So why tail him?
At a minimum, he's awol.
Why not just detain him and turn him
over to the military police?
Because he's got something on me.
He knows I lied on the
report about his death.
So you're trying to
catch him in a fresh crime,
arrest him for what he's doing now.
Exactly.
Cool.
I'm in.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
I got your back, boo.
You're having a baby?
That's so great.
That's not what I said.
I said Bailey wants to have a baby.
And you don't, because you're ol... der
and feel like your child
raising years are behind you?
Look, I loved raising Henry.
It was incredible.
But there is a lot I want
to accomplish on the job,
and I don't have a lot of
time left, because I am older.
Ok, I get that, but have you seen babies?
They're so cute, and I feel like you
should have like three.
Ok.
I am deleting Bailey's
number from your phone.
We're being assigned to assist
city safe la in cleaning
up an encampment
of unhoused residents.
La county sheriff is bringing
a group of inmates to assist.
Ma'am?
Excuse me, ma'am? I cannot let you
- everything ok?
- Yeah.
No.
He won't let me bring
drinks to my daughter
and her friends.
Come on. They're dying in this heat.
Ma'am, it is 70 degrees.
Is your daughter homeless?
No, she's one of the inmates.
- Mom.
- Honey.
Hey.
Trustee, get back here.
I missed you.
Me too.
You smell good.
Ooh, you don't, but I still love you.
No contact.
Ok, hey, hey, what's the harm?
We're literally surrounded by police.
You're not the one who has to search her
for contraband after this.
You, leave.
You, back to work.
See you in two weeks.
Yeah.
I hope you have a horrible day.
Give me the bag. Let it go.
Let it go. Let it go.
- Hey. - Give it...
- hey. - Let it go.
Hey, what's going on?
She's trying to steal my bag.
Sir, no she's not, ok?
We're going to pack up your belongings
- and send them to the shelter.
- Yeah, yeah.
That's the same thing you said last time.
When I got my tent back, it
was ripped in three places.
Ok, how about we let
him hold on to the bag
for a little bit?
Whoa, hang on. Hang on.
Thank you.
Give it to me... sir, back up.
Hey, officer Nolan?
Do you remember
the Karina Lewis case?
Yeah.
College gymnast, boyfriend
murdered her a few years back,
but the body was never found.
Yeah.
This is her bag.
It went missing along with her.
Sir, where did you get this bag?
Hey, I found that.
I swear.
This place just became a crime scene.
Lock it down.
Officer Nolan?
What now?
I just found these in the garbage can.
And one of the prisoners just escaped.
- So, where'd you get this?
- Well, I didn't steal it.
Y'all assume just
because we're homeless
I don't assume anything, but stealing it
is better than taking it off a murder victim
making yourself a suspect.
Yeah, well, it was neither
of those things, all right?
I found the bag in Griffith park last week.
- I can show you where.
- Ok.
Good. Let's go.
You're riding with me.
Yes, ma'am.
Payoff.
Maybe he's smuggling
something into the country.
Or out.
Or maybe ray lost a bet and is innocent.
I mean, you've been
following this guy for two days
and haven't seen
anything remotely criminal.
How long are you going to keep this up?
- As long as it takes.
- Really?
You just walk away from your job,
your relationship with Lucy
to arrest a guy you haven't
thought about in a decade?
Yeah.
What?
If you lied on a report, you
must have had a good reason.
I was trying to protect
Ray's family so they'd
- get his death benefits.
- Noble.
Lucy would understand that.
Yeah, but she'd still get
in trouble if she didn't notify
ia about my transgression.
True.
This is very irritating.
I don't think you're just protecting her.
I think you're protecting yourself.
There's something else you
did that you don't want to admit.
And you're basing this on?
I'm your bff.
I know you.
I'm a grown man.
I don't have bffs.
Technically, you can only have one bff.
I'm going to take a closer look.
Wait.
Come on.
Mystery man had diplomatic plates.
We follow him or stay with ray?
Ray.
I can ask my friend at state
for help iding the new player.
Missing inmate is Teresa Vaughn,
the girl you allowed to make contact
- with a potential accomplice.
- Ok.
You're blaming me because
you failed to do your job?
What the hell did you say?
Ok.
We can play the blame game later.
Right now, we have a fugitive to find.
I agree it's most likely the
mother that helped her escape.
That's our first lead.
We can put a bolo out for Theresa.
Why was Theresa incarcerated?
Assault, but she only had
ten days left on her sentence.
That doesn't make any sense.
Trying to escape would
add at least a year.
Why risk it?
I was just reviewing the
details in Karina's case.
She disappeared 19 months ago.
Boyfriend was the immediate suspect.
He ultimately confessed to strangling her
in his apartment down in culver city,
then he claims he blacked
out afterwards and forgot
where he left the body.
Any of this looking familiar to you?
Yeah, a little.
I was trying to find a place to sleep.
Everything was so wet
because of the storm,
but it was around here though.
You know, a big flat rock.
There.
There it is right there.
Behind there.
It was all muddy when I went through it.
I was hoping to find some
cash or some food on the inside,
but there was only a
couple of schoolbooks.
Yeah, the rain could
have dislodged the bag
causing it to go downhill.
Karina Lewis.
Well, at least now her family
can give her a proper burial.
You said the boyfriend
confessed to strangling her?
Yeah.
Then why is there a
bullet wound in her head?
That's a small caliber, ...22, maybe .38.
Why confess to the murder
but lie about the method?
It makes no sense.
Teresa Vaughn was
serving six months for assault
on a woman she claimed was
hooking up with her boyfriend.
I'm not sure that's the
person I'd be assaulting.
Not that violence is ever the answer.
7-Adam-15, 7-Adam-6
pulled over your bolo alert.
Brenda Vaughn, fugitive's
mother, third and oak.
Copy that.
Show us responding.
No sign of the fugitive.
- I told you.
- Thank you.
Would you mind going to her house
in case the daughter
decides to show up there?
You got it.
I get how this looks,
but I had nothing to do
with my daughter's escape.
Any idea where your
daughter might have gone?
No.
But any place is better than jail, right?
Not when you have two
weeks left on your sentence.
Why would she throw that away now?
Did you say something to
her, tell her a secret when
- you were giving her a hug?
- No.
Ok, so then you just
expect me to believe it's
a coincidence she escaped
right after you showed up?
I can't control what you
believe, but it's the truth.
Do you have kids?
Yeah, I have one.
Then you understand that I would
do anything to help my daughter,
including practicing tough love, ok?
If Teresa asked me to help her escape,
I would have told her it is the
dumbest idea I'd ever heard
and just suck it up and finish her time.
Any idea who might help your daughter
despite the consequences?
She has a lot of friends,
but I doubt any of them
would stick their necks out for her.
- What about the boyfriend?
- Mike?
No.
He broke up with her right
after she attacked Doreen.
That's where.
That's where what?
Teresa is still pissed about the affair.
She told me she was planning
on doing some permanent damage
to Doreen when she got out.
Control, I'm going to need
an address on a Doreen...
- Davis.
Home and work.
Doreen?
Yeah.
What's going on?
Teresa Vaughn escaped
from custody this morning.
Escaped?
Yeah, but we're going
to make sure you're safe.
Yeah, you don't need to.
Teresa came by like half an hour ago,
said that she got released early.
Apologized for everything.
Said that she should have
listened to me when I said
- I didn't hook up with Mike.
- Wait.
So there was no affair?
No. Mike and I were friends.
That's it.
But he was definitely
cheating on her with someone.
Well, did she say where
she was going next?
No.
Just she finally knew who to blame.
You're too close.
I can't tail him by nose
with only one vehicle.
- Need to keep him in sight.
- We're going to get made.
- You should let me drive.
- I got it.
I come in peace.
Who's your friend?
Ooh.
Hey, mama.
I thought you said this guy
was smart because all I see
is slick.
What's the plan here, sarge?
You just going to follow
me around all week while I
wait for my mom to kick it?
Yeah, we both know
you're not here for your mom.
Mark bailed on you?
Did he lose his nerve?
Maybe you did.
Was there a falling out
over what to do with me?
Let me guess, he
was team extermination
and you were team justice.
You know, this guy's nickname
in the service was the reaper.
It's sad when one of your
heroes grows a conscience.
I'm going to go now.
I'm open to some
company if you want a lift.
I'll pass, but we'll be
seeing you again real soon.
Can't wait.
Thank you for meeting with us.
Yeah, no problem.
Actually, you could help
me out with something.
I have to approve a headshot
for my campaign website.
Which one of these looks
more district attorney-ish?
The one on the right.
I agree.
We need to talk about a case
that you prosecuted last year.
Karina Lewis.
Karina Lewis?
Yeah, the boyfriend strangled her,
full confession.
He pled out, doing 20 at soledad.
Right.
Well, we found her remains today.
Well, hey, that's great news.
The family can finally put her to rest.
Yes, but the only problem
is, she was not strangled.
She was shot in the head with a .22.
Boyfriend lied in his statement.
Right, which clearly was coerced.
Officer thorsen is
getting ahead of himself,
but it is a significant inconsistency.
Is there any chance it
was a false confession?
No.
Are you serious?
That fast, just no?
Officer thorsen, wait
for me outside, please?
- Ma'am...
- go.
Now.
I apologize.
He clearly has brought some
of his own history into this.
Look, you weren't there,
detective, and neither was he.
The investigation was solid.
The boyfriend had a history of violence.
Hair matching the victim was
found in the trunk of his car.
Witnesses heard them arguing.
I could have gotten a conviction
even without his confession.
So kindly invite officer thorsen
to take his self-righteousness and stick it
where the sun don't shine.
Are we done here?
Yes, sir.
Is he really not going to do anything?
You cannot talk to a prosecutor like that.
Detective... ever.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Does this mean we're
abandoning the investigation?
There is no we in this, officer thorsen.
This is not our investigation.
It is mine, which means
that the risk of pissing off
someone who will likely
be the next district attorney
falls on me.
Ok.
Does this mean you're
abandoning the investigation?
No.
It means that we need to
find undeniable evidence
that Karina Lewis was killed by someone
other than the guy who is currently
sitting in prison before we can even
think about coming back here.
Why are you smiling?
Because you said we.
Were there any other suspects
aside from the boyfriend?
Yeah.
A guy used to work with
Karina at her off-campus job,
Ryan Jones.
And fun fact, the detective
that interviewed him said Ryan
was quite the gun collector.
So it is likely he would own a .22.
Exactly.
In my professional opinion,
his alibi was super shaky.
Need I remind you, five minutes,
that your professional opinion
is still a work in progress?
Noted.
But Ryan claimed he was hanging out
at his girlfriend's apartment.
That is a little shaky.
But it is nowhere near
enough to move the needle.
Kids here?
They're at my mom's.
Wes is going to pick them up
on his way home, which makes
this the perfect time for
you to tell me why you
think this is all your fault.
I don't.
Come on.
Sit.
There is no way you let a
loser like ray live under your skin
if you didn't blame
yourself for more than just
lying on a report.
Look, I had been squad
leader most of my second tour,
top performance ratings,
fast track to a promotion,
unless my battalion
commander found out
that a soldier in my unit was engaged
in rampant criminality.
I thought if I brought ray in myself,
I could keep it within the squad.
No harm, no foul, and
I would be sergeant
first class in no time.
So we went after him,
unsanctioned, under the radar.
We located him in a
village just outside of mosul.
As soon as he found out he was trapped,
he called in an air
strike right on top of us.
It was like the world exploded.
I thought I was going to die, Angela.
But I got lucky.
The Humvee that Mark and I
were behind, it saved us but,
but Henderson and coyle,
they were blown apart.
I still don't know how ray survived.
I mean, the building he was in,
it was almost completely destroyed.
There... we found his mangled
dog tags in the wreckage.
I mean, there was...
there was so much blood.
Without question,
we thought he was kia.
I mean, it was... it was
a spectacular failure
of leadership.
I put my career above my oath and
two soldiers, two decent men,
didn't come home that night.
And I'm going to have to live with that
for the rest of my life.
What are you still doing here?
I'm just going over
the Karina Lewis case.
Right. I heard they found her body.
Detectives questioned
this guy for over ten hours
without his lawyer, right?
He's young.
He's scared.
In retrospect, it's possible
he could have been coerced.
Ok.
So take another look.
If he was, get the conviction overturned.
It's not that simple.
Because you're running for da.
Yeah.
And how's it going to look
when it comes out that you
railroaded an innocent man?
Hey, I didn't railroad anybody.
This was a very solid case.
Based on a possibly
questionable confession.
Yeah.
You really dove in.
Yeah, I wanted to make
an informed decision.
And?
And I'm more sure than ever.
I want to have a baby.
And you don't.
And I don't know.
Some days, this job is all I can handle.
When I had Henry, I was the boss.
I never had to miss a school play or
a parent-teacher conference.
I don't have that now, which means
I can't be the kind of dad I want to be
or the cop I want to be.
So that's a no.
It's a big decision.
I just... I need more than
a day to think about it.
Well, if you are trying to figure out a way
to let me down easy, don't.
The longer you let me
have hope, the more painful
it'll be.
Just in time.
I ordered pizza.
Thank you.
I have been dreading having to cook.
Any news on the Tim front?
Not yet.
So I'm just practicing
trust, Patience, and I hate it.
That was quick.
I'm going to get changed.
Hey, there.
I'm ray.
Tim's friend.
He's not here.
That's cool.
Lucy?
Yeah?
Can I help you?
I hope so.
You Tim's girlfriend?
You don't need that.
I'm here to help you, not hurt you.
Yeah.
I think I'm going to pass.
You need to leave.
Tim never mentioned me?
I have no idea who you are.
So how would I know if he
has mentioned you or not?
Why don't you call Tim?
Ask him about mosul.
The only phone call I'm going to make
is for an ambulance
to wheel you out of here
unless you get out right now.
No problem.
You tell Tim to take a knee.
I'm going to be gone in a few days,
unless he gives me a
reason to stick around.
Who the hell is that guy?
What?
Hey, what's wrong?
Where are you?
Lucy.
Where the hell are you?
What happened?
Your buddy ray stopped by.
Are you ok?
Do I look ok?
Let's give them a minute.
What if Tamara had
been there by herself
- when that creep showed up?
- I'm sorry.
- I had no idea.
- No!
No. No more excuses, Tim.
You have to tell me
what's going on with you.
Right now.
Now!
His name is ray Watkins.
He was under my command in Iraq.
I thought he was killed
in action, but he's back,
and he's going to hurt someone if I
don't do something about it.
None of that
none of it explains why you cut me off.
No.
It doesn't.
Stop trying to protect me, Tim!
I'm sorry. I can't, ok?
I won't.
- You read Lopez in.
- It's different.
How?
She has less to lose than you.
Please, just steer
clear of this for me, ok?
I can't.
I won't.
You clearly need help, and I am done
being the good girlfriend, ok?
You don't have to tell me everything,
but you are going to let me in.
She is about a year old now, right?
Yeah, that's right.
So she's sleeping pretty good?
You really do not remember what
it is like to have young kids, do you?
No, I guess I don't.
I'm running on a cold
brew and adrenaline,
but it's worth it.
Right.
Why, are you and Bailey
thinking about having a kid?
She is.
I just don't know that I
can juggle a kid and the job.
Well, I manage. So does Lopez.
- So did grey.
- Right.
But you're younger.
So was he.
Just starting out in your careers.
I am a little late to the party.
I've got maybe ten years
to maximize my career
before it's all but over.
Look, it's a cliché, because it is true.
There's really never a
good time to have a kid.
But you know, you make it work.
Thank you.
I know who was sleeping
with Teresa's boyfriend.
So this is her and Mike last
year before she was arrested.
Anything look familiar?
Teresa's mom was
wearing that shirt yesterday.
And Teresa said she smelled great.
Yeah, because she
smelled like her boyfriend,
and she didn't realize it until after.
And when she figured
it out, she lost her mind
and took off.
But why go apologize
to Doreen and not go
straight to her mom's place?
Well, we've had a shop
parked outside her mom's place
since she escaped.
But not Mike's place.
Miss Marcos, thanks for
coming in on short notice.
Of course.
You mentioned this had something
to do with that horrible
Karina Lewis murder?
Yes.
Your boyfriend at the time, Ryan Jones,
he used to work with
Karina. Is that right?
Yes.
And according to your statement,
the night of the murder he
was with you having dinner.
Do you recall what time he arrived?
I don't know.
Whatever I said back then must be right.
Well, you said 6:00 P.M.
Ok.
Then it was 6:00.
Why am I here?
They caught the guy.
We actually have
new evidence indicating
that he might be innocent,
new evidence that implicates Ryan.
He said it... it wasn't a big deal.
He said that it would
make things easier if I just
said he was there at 6:00.
What time did you actually
see Ryan that night?
Not until 9:00.
Officer thorsen?
A word.
Yes, ma'am.
Excuse me.
She just blew up Ryan's alibi.
He's our guy.
What are you doing interviewing
a witness without me?
I'm sorry.
I should have notified you.
Are you really this dense or are you just
actively trying to jam me up?
No, it's not about you.
This is about an innocent
man sitting in prison.
Ok, listen, I know that this
case is personal for you.
But if you keep going rogue,
you are going to ruin this man's chances
of ever being released, ok?
The paths to a new
trial are incredibly narrow
and almost all procedural.
New evidence, even
overwhelming evidence,
does not guarantee his release.
Ok.
Well, that's not right.
No, it is not, but it is the
system that we are working in,
which means that every step needs
to be carefully considered.
Ok.
Well, Ryan's girlfriend just
admitted to lying for him.
She didn't see him until 9:00 that night.
So what's our next step?
Ok.
We... we need a murder weapon.
If we can match the
ballistics from a .22 in Ryan's
possession with the bullet
that the me found in Karina,
then we have a case.
But to get the gun, we
need probable cause
to get a warrant.
And right now, we do not have that.
Brenda's here.
I wasn't even... sounds
like Teresa is here too.
You liar.
You're my mom.
My fricking mom!
Control, 7-Adam-15 we have an on view
4-15 family at 1331 Arlington.
You got her pregnant?
I thought you didn't even want kids.
Honestly, I'm with Teresa at this point.
Right. It's just a bat.
Let's split up.
I'm going to go around back.
Wait.
Look at her waistband.
Come on, say that's enough.
All right, that changes things.
She's enraged.
It's going to be hard
to get her to calm down.
Get back to the cruiser.
I want you to come racing in hot after 30
seconds, lights and sirens.
Copy that.
Augh!
Police.
You're under arrest.
And for the record, you
are a terrible mother.
Hey, my guy at state came through.
Diplomatic plates we sent him
belong to the Turkish embassy,
but the guy in the car wasn't Turkish.
He was Venezuelan.
Gustav Martinez, military
counterintelligence.
Specialty is cracking
down on anyone considered
an enemy of the state.
Dissidents.
If ray met with Gustav,
it had to be for a job.
Makes sense.
Gustav can't operate domestically,
so he hires ray to kidnap
or kill anyone on the outs
at home.
According to my guy,
the most likely candidate
is Elena a cost a, political activist.
Hello?
This is sergeant Tim
Bradford with the LAPD.
We just received a
credible threat on your life.
They're here.
Yell the name ray Watkins right now.
- Do it.
- Ray Watkins.
Ray Watkins. Ray Watkins.
No.
Ray Watkins.
Hey, Tim.
We know about the Venezuelans, ray,
so let Elena go right
now, and I'll push the da's
office to go easy on you.
Sorry, buddy, I got a job to
do and a reputation to uphold.
We're gonna have
to let this one play out.
Catch me if you can.
All right, put her inside.
I'll let Neil know the
container is ready to load.
- Get on the ground.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Now.
- It's over, ray.
- Stop.
Show me your hands right now.
Got your entire crew in custody.
Should have changed it up
after you caught me following you.
Yeah, I get a little cocky sometimes.
I didn't know you'd be on me this early.
You know killing me
is your only play here.
I'm not going to kill you, ray.
And there's no air strike
you can call in this time.
Are you kidding?
I am the air strike.
I'm about to blow up your whole life.
Sergeant Bradford, this is a dii,
or department initiated investigation,
which could result in discipline.
Your continued
employment with the LAPD
is contingent on your
full and truthful answers
to my questions.
I understand.
I want to be clear.
Other people will deal with your crimes.
I'm not questioning you as a suspect.
My job is to investigate your accusations
against sergeant Bradford.
On that point, I am crystal clear.
When did you become aware
that ray Watkins was alive?
Last week.
I saw him entering a 7-Eleven.
Bradford and Mark
greer tracked me down,
threatened me in my mother's home.
Was your mother there to witness that?
Yeah, but she's in the hospital.
Doctors say it will be a
miracle if she wakes up.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
But Mark, he was there.
I haven't seen Mark greer in a decade.
I still get the occasional Christmas card.
According to the faa,
there's no record of Mark
greer flying into Los Angeles.
No local credit card charges.
His phone never left
Arlington, and the army
shows him as on base
for the entire two weeks.
Clever man.
He was planning to kill
me, so he covered his tracks.
Did I conspire to
commit murder with a guy
I haven't seen in ten years?
No.
So ray Watkins is lying.
Little tip when dealing with
ray, if his lips are moving,
he's lying.
Tim lied on the after action report.
He said I was killed in action.
I look dead to you?
Why would I lie?
My whole squad had
been hit with friendly fire.
I had lost three of my men.
Technically, two.
Right, but I didn't know
that until a few days ago.
And it shook me.
Ray Watkins was awol.
Why not contact military police
when you learned he was alive?
I wanted to be sure
before I sounded the alarm.
Here's the truth.
Bradford wanted to protect his career,
so he lied about what actually happened.
He participated in a
cover-up, and he knowingly
falsified official reports.
These are serious accusations.
Is any part of what ray said true?
No.
None of it.
Hi.
Excuse me?
I'm so sorry to interrupt,
but what are you using?
44 Magnum.
Is it heavy?
You tell me.
Wow, you must be
really strong to hold that.
I lift.
Ok.
So I am trying to decide on what to buy,
and I want something that's light
but still, like, accurate.
38 is a good option.
Ok, I've heard of that.
A friend of mine, she has a
.22 rutger, and she loves it.
She says it's light enough
to hold in her purse.
Ruger.
A ruger. Right.
Yeah.
22 is a good choice for a
delicate woman like you.
No recoil.
Ok.
Do you have one I could try?
Please?
Yeah, sure.
I have a few with me.
Yeah. Ok.
Thank you.
Wow.
That is super light.
Can I?
Yeah? Ok.
So I had a chance to look
over the ballistics report.
The bullets that you collected
are a match for the bullet
that killed Karina Lewis.
An arrest warrant has been approved,
and I will be signing a
motion to vacate the conviction.
Really?
Yeah, I wouldn't have prosecuted if we'd
had this evidence at the time.
That's awesome.
No.
I probably shouldn't hug you, right?
Right.
Let us know if you need anything.
Will do.
And thank you.
No.
Thank you for sticking with it.
Good job.
And your campaign?
Well, doing the right thing,
no matter how difficult,
should be seen as a
character strength, not a flaw.
Nice.
You float that one by the advisors yet?
Damn right I did, and they loved it.
I bet they did.
Big plans this weekend?
Hide in my room, wear
blinders to the kitchen.
I need to move?
Definitely.
What about you?
What's going on with
the whole, baby situation?
Mostly I've just been avoiding
thinking about it all day.
And now?
And now, having a kid...
Has been the greatest joy of my life.
So why would I want to deny her that?
In light of Ray's numerous crimes,
his statements against you
appear retaliatory in nature.
Because your after action reports
have been accepted as
factual by your military superiors,
which there's no evidence
to suggest otherwise,
this dii is closed with a
finding of not sustained.
Thank you, sir.
- Always a pleasure.
- Yeah.
We should get the wives together soon,
have some dinner.
I would love that.
You know this isn't over.
I know.
You violated procedure
in pursuit of a suspect
and roped in two other officers?
What if Ms. Acosta had been killed
because you didn't utilize
proper channels and resources?
It was wrong.
I know.
I'm required to notify
your Metro commander.
What she does with it is up to her.
- Sir...
- you're dismissed.
Come here.
How did it go with ia?
I lied about everything.
But I mean, it saved my job, right?
Protected you and Lopez.
It was an impossible situation.
I would have done the same
thing if I was in your place.
You wouldn't have been in my place.
You never would have put
self-interest over your team.
You thought you could handle it.
You were wrong, but you
made it right, so it's fine.
Yeah. I wish it was that easy.
Lucy, I just lied to two
men I deeply respect, ok?
I just betrayed everything I thought
- was right about myself.
- Tim.
No, no.
You got to let me finish, ok?
This is very hard for me to say.
Ok.
Lucy, I've been lying
to myself for a long time.
That's clear to me now, and I can't
I can't just go back
to the way things were.
Not right now.
Maybe never.
Wait.
Are you breaking up with me?
I'm sorry.
You don't... you don't get to do that.
You don't get to lie to me
and then use that as an excuse
to leave me, ok?
- That's not ok.
- I know.
- What you're doing is not ok.
I know.
You... you are an incredible person.
No.
No, you're incredible, ok?
You deserve so much better.
My god.
That's why I'm walking away.
Don't do this.
Why are you doing this?
I'm sorry.
Are you learning baby sign language?
Maybe.
How about we just
forget about the elephant
in the room for tonight,
make some dinner,
and enjoy some time together?
I think that's a great idea.
But you may want to lay
off the wine if I'm going to get
you pregnant later tonight.
Is that what we're doing?
Yes, with much enthusiasm.
Are you sure?
Hydrating.
Do we have to wait till after dinner?
Nope.
Grab my water.
Thank you.
You're in trouble.
Damn it.