Dispatch said it was a noise complaint?
Yes, sir.
And they requested us specifically?
That's what she said.
I guess we missed it.
This would be a great opportunity
to teach me about de-escalating
in policing.
Imagine my surprise when reviewing
last week's bodycam footage and I saw
this.
No. Yes, sir.
I... well, I
I can explain. It's.
I'm waiting.
Wake up, lazybones.
We're gettin' married tomorrow,
and there is a butt load to get done.
I'm not feeling very good.
- What?
- Yeah, my head.
- What's going on?
- Maybe...
Sucker!
- You faker.
- Yeah.
Listen, this is important.
We're getting married tomorrow.
I know. I already said that.
Yeah, I just felt like it needed
a little extra attention.
- Get your ass out of bed.
- Yes, boss.
We need to go meet
the wedding planner.
Yes, boss.
Henry, hi.
Hey, Bailey.
Are you getting on your flight?
No. A little hiccup.
My flight got canceled.
Technically, the entire airline
went bankrupt, so...
Okay, well, we're just gonna have
to get you on another flight.
I tried, but there are none available
that'll get me there
in time for the wedding.
- Who are you talking to?
- The firehouse.
We are not gonna tell your dad about this
because I don't want him to worry.
Okay, I need you to get
to the train station.
It looks like there's
a few flights out of Haneda
that would get you here in time,
but you need to make
the next bullet train.
On it. Thanks for the assist.
- Everything okay?
- Yeah, totally.
They couldn't find something,
so instead of actually looking,
they call me.
- Men.
- Tell me about it.
- Shall we plan a wedding?
- Yes.
Chastity, hi!
Pete. Not Pete. Randy.
Hello, mein bestest Freund.
Wow. Funniest of stories.
So when I skip-tracer-bounty-hunted
Mr. Peter yesterday,
he begged me not to take him in
because of your upcoming
marital consummation.
Skip traced for what?
Outstanding warrant.
6,000 in unpaid parking tickets.
- 6,000?
- Yeah.
Yeah, when I told him I took a vow
as a law enforcement officer
not to accept bribes,
he made me promise to go
to your wedding in his place.
And have sexy time with his girlfriend?
Just over-the-clothes stuff.
I'm teaching Randy here
how to be a better kisser.
She is very good.
Allow me to share her skills.
- No. No.
- That's okay.
We're actually running late
to meet the wedding planners.
Well, this is insane, to be honest.
But we've really gotta go.
So the guest room is ready to go.
Please stay out of trouble.
You are no fun, but you will be tonight
at your bachelor party.
No bachelor party.
I told you... I told Pete.
Yeah, and he said, "Well, I can't believe"
"we are related, half-bro.
- "Pound."
- Nailed it.
But while I am so glad that you are here,
I, in no way, agree to participate
in this bizarre brother-swap thing,
- so you can cut that out...
- Okay.
You can have a lovely day,
and you can come with me.
- Yes.
- Thank you, guys.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
- Okay, we are alone.
- Yeah.
What would Mr. Peter do?
Um...
- Role-play.
- Yes.
I will be Marlene Dietrich.
You will be Marty McFly,
teaming up with Mr. Frodo
to help him get to Mordor.
- Thank you for breakfast.
- Of course.
But you didn't have to walk me home.
I didn't. I came to check on Aaron.
All right.
- I'll see you tonight.
- Okay.
Remember, I have book group,
so I'll be home late.
You just had book group.
How many books
do you guys read a week?
Two or three.
Now where can I find Aaron?
Thank you. Bye, baby.
- Bye, baby.
- Mwah.
And turn to the right.
Wish we had a better lighting setup,
but this tells a story.
Hi.
Mrs. Grey, hey.
How you feeling?
Good. Great.
Wish I could just get back out there.
I understand.
But don't rush.
No matter what Wade might say,
it took him a while to get himself right
after he was shot.
No one's gonna judge you negatively.
Appreciate that. Thanks.
Well, I'm gonna get going.
Of course. Thanks for checking in. Yeah.
- Hey.
- You have a sec?
- Sure.
No. Sorry, we gotta get out there.
Everything all right?
Yeah. Totally. It can wait.
Get your ass in the shop.
You are driving while
I figure out your new nickname.
Yes, ma'am.
- Got a minute to talk?
- Sure.
There's nothing to talk about.
You felt I undermined you
at a crime scene
to stop you from making detective.
I explained that I didn't.
- Now we're moving on.
- Okay.
Well, while I appreciate the efficiency,
that's not how actual
healthy communication works.
Wow, that's not condescending at all.
Explain to me what there is to talk about
that isn't just a retread
of what I just efficiently covered?
Well... that's not the point.
Look, if I have to start
another deep undercover assignment,
there are real issues here
that we need to talk about.
Which we will deal with
if they come up then.
I gotta get to work.
Have a good shift.
This is a problem.
It's amazing you got it last-minute,
but it's so much more
than a home wedding.
- And by more, you mean...
- Expensive.
If we bring the same game plan
here as your house,
it'll look cheap and low-rent.
So we have to up everything...
flowers, catering.
I'm a little worried about
how stressed out you seem.
Sorry, it's been a morning.
My girlfriend is cheating,
and my assistant quit.
- Well, we're happy to help.
- Great.
I need you to go give Be-Bop $1,000.
- Love it. Who's Be-Bop?
- Our DJ.
I am so sorry,
I just have to take this quick.
Hey, what's up?
- Where are you?
- I'm doing wedding stuff.
You forgot about the deposition.
I forgot about the deposition.
You have to get me out of that.
There's so much to do.
I'm getting married tomorrow.
Look, I get it, but Judge Scott was born
without sympathy.
Wesley.
Looking sharp.
- Sharp.
- Ha.
I can try to get Oscar's lawyer
to agree to a continuance,
but only when you're here.
I'll be there in 20 minutes.
Be where in 20?
It's a surprise, but I will meet you
at the DJ's house.
- Okay, no problem.
- Gotcha.
Henry. Hey, what's happenin'?
You missed the bullet train.
Those things go quick.
Okay, just give me a second
to figure out a plan C.
You have always hated him.
He won't stop barking.
You take point, Miss Cleo.
Mi... right, the psychic. Good one.
Who called 911?
That was me, because
this bitch poisoned my dog.
I did not.
Can I take a look at him?
Yeah, of course. He's a sweetheart.
He's a menace.
But I didn't hurt him, I swear.
It's okay.
It looks like he was chewing
on your planter.
Detective, can you look at this?
Thank you.
Um, where did you get this flowerpot?
The farmers market last weekend.
Why?
Okay, we need to have it tested.
Officer Juarez will give you a receipt.
You need to take your dog to the vet
and let them know that he might
have ingested a narcotic.
- Wesley.
- John-O.
It's great to see you.
I'm sorry for upsetting
and disrupting your upcoming nuptials.
Although truth be told, I'm a little hurt
I didn't get the invite.
Is that why you're suing me?
No.
I'm suing you for gross negligence
in allowing my injury while
selflessly donating a kidney.
Oscar, you are so full of...
Don't talk to my client like that.
Monica.
Good morning.
I'm taking over Mr. Hutchinson's case.
Substitution of counsel
has been filed with the court.
Let's get started.
You're in trouble now.
Aaron. Look, I'm sorry about earlier.
You know how judgy Harper can be,
and I really need to impress her.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Just, um, having a hard day.
It's okay.
You're safe.
Boot, I thought you were going to 10-1.
No, yes, ma'am. I'll be out there in five.
Make it two.
So how's it going
with the department shrink?
Good.
Should be cleared any day now.
Officer Lucy Chen, wow.
How fortunate to find you here.
Fortunate for who?
We have ein winzig problem
and need a little help.
Randy pawned Bailey's wedding ring.
What? Why would you do that?
I was role-playing as Pete
and got a little carried away.
And unfortunately,
before I could buy it back,
a murderous-looking man
bought it out from under me.
So we really need you to, um...
- Get it back?
- Exactly. Wow!
See, I told you we have come
to the right location.
Please help us.
Immediately.
Hey.
Do you have any leverage
with a felon called The Hammer?
No, why?
Okay, so Skip Tracer Randy
was role-playing
as Nolan's brother Pete,
and he pawned Bailey's wedding ring,
and The Hammer bought it.
Nothing about that sentence
makes sense.
I've run The Hammer before.
You want no part of his craziness.
Yet I still told Randy
that I would try and get it for him, so
I'll go with you.
No. Please don't do me any favors.
Seriously?
I knew you weren't gonna
be able to let it go.
I have completely let it go.
Let what go?
Nothing.
Okay, do you want my help or not?
I don't need it, but I will accept it.
- Fine.
- Good.
- Whatever.
- Great.
- Let's go.
- Maybe I'll go too.
Grab some popcorn on the way
for the show.
- You're not funny.
- I'm hysterical.
Ask Wesley.
Failure to protect my client is a violation
of the Eighth Amendment,
not to mention depriving him
of minimal civilized measures
of life's necessities.
- He got takeout.
- I got assaulted.
And you let it happen.
Look, I don't have time for this.
How about a little bit
of human decency here, Monica?
Officer Nolan has a wedding
to get ready for.
If you agree to the continuance,
the judge will sign off.
Happy to.
If Officer Nolan turns over his phone.
- What?
- No, no, no.
That is ridiculous.
His phone contains evidence
in texts, photos, and notes consistent
with a cruel indifference
to my client's suffering.
No, it doesn't.
And I worry that he will
destroy that evidence
if given the opportunity.
Okay, there is no nexus between
the plaintiff's alleged discomfort
and Officer Nolan's phone.
And any such intrusion is so vast
that only a special master
should be allowed
to review the contents of that phone.
Then it looks like
we're spending the day here.
No, I-I can't.
Just... look, I'm gonna
give Wesley my phone.
The judge can decide what to share.
Great seeing you, John.
Congratulations.
I just need to write down one address.
Why didn't you answer my call?
- Lost my phone.
- What? Where?
At the surprise place.
John, the next 24 hours are gonna hit us
at 100 miles an hour.
I need you to have a phone.
No. Yeah. I know. Don't worry.
I'm gonna get one right after
we're finished here.
I won't skip a beat.
Okay.
- Who is it?
- John Nolan.
You're gonna DJ our wedding tomorrow.
Yeah, yeah. It's open. Come on in.
Hey, what's up?
Listen, I've been thinking
a lot about your gig
because I know
that you said you wanted me
to lean into, like,
a '90s Janet vibe or whatever.
But I just got this old Nordic go-go disk.
You gotta check this out
because I really think
this is gonna set...
You know switchblades are illegal
in the state of California, right?
- Really?
- Yeah.
It's a violation of Penal Code 21510,
but I can ignore that.
We're just here to give you
the cash for the gig.
Hey, what's up? No. No, no, no.
You tell him that he's gotta pay up.
I boosted those kicks
'cause he said he wanted them.
Do I look like I have size 7 feet to you?
Now he's bragging about shoplifting.
Why don't you just wait outside?
- I think that's for the best.
- Yeah.
I'm sorry, you guys said
that you were here
for the... the DJ gig or some molly?
Okay. And that's a felony.
We were here for the DJ gig,
but seeing as how I'm a cop
and you just committed
several crimes in front of me,
now I'm here to arrest you.
All right, good news, bad news.
The Hammer,
aka William Robert Bennett,
has an outstanding felony warrant.
Wait, his name is Billy Bob Bennett?
Correct.
No wonder he prefers his nickname.
Can I finish the whole
good news/bad news cliché?
Yes. Sorry, knock yourself out.
The Hammer has a felony warrant,
which means we can go
kick down his door right now.
Which is good,
but he bought the ring legally.
Which is bad, because
he's under no obligation
to give it to us, and I'd argue
he's even less inclined
to hand it over once we arrest him.
Plus...
Plus what?
Plus, The Hammer
is called The Hammer
because he likes to fight.
And there's no one he loves
to fight more than cops.
Well, after you.
No, ladies first.
Oh. Um, just wait. Hear us out.
Earlier today, you bought
a wedding ring at a pawn shop.
Yeah. I'm getting married in a month.
Congratulations.
Unfortunately, that ring was stolen,
and we... we will need it back.
Well, I paid 1,000 bucks for it.
Right, which is why we are willing
to make a trade with you today.
You give us the ring
and we will give you a head start.
She's lying.
She's not.
You give it to us, we head
back down to the shop,
we'll wait 20 minutes
before we call for backup.
You can make a run for it,
grab the missus-to-be, head to ground.
Right.
Nah.
Why not?
Because eventually,
I'm gonna get caught.
But you needing something from me,
now, that's an opportunity.
What kind of opportunity?
A fair fight for once.
You beat me, I'll give you the ring
and I put your cuffs on.
I beat you,
I get to keep the ring
and I still put the cuffs on.
No fight, no ring.
Guess you're gonna have to fight him.
I have to look amazing
in a dress tomorrow.
Nobody cares what you look like.
He's huge. I am not fighting him.
Let's go.
Yes!
- You got this.
- Thanks.
My God.
All right! You win.
You win. You win.
The ring's in the drawer over there.
That's good.
Here.
Good job.
Yeah, thanks.
Yeah.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm great.
Got your text. What's up?
A tox screen came back
on that hinky flowerpot.
Pure heroin.
That the skell that our homeowner
bought the flowerpot from?
Yep, Seth Gallegos.
Couple misdemeanor priors.
You want help taking a run at him?
No, I'm gonna get the rookie to do it.
Yeah, see what she's got.
And you invited me to watch the show.
Gracias.
Mr. Gallegos, thank you for coming in.
Didn't think I had a choice.
No, you absolutely do.
I just was hoping you can
clear up a few things.
Let's start easy.
Do you sell these at
the Silverlake Farmers Market?
I don't know.
No, I don't.
Seth.
I think you know you're in trouble here.
We tested the flowerpots.
It's made of compressed heroin.
I don't know what that is.
You don't know what heroin is?
All right, let's just cut to the chase.
You're a low-level drug mule,
most likely working for the crew
that converts the flowerpots
into street product.
You figured nobody would miss
the real flowerpots
that are packed in the front of the truck
to hide the fake ones,
so you started selling them.
But you sold the wrong planters.
How am I doing?
You do know that El Jefe
is going to be homicidal
when he finds out you stole from him.
I didn't steal.
I don't steal. I'm not a thief.
And I don't know
what you're talking about.
A drug mule? What?
Listen, you have more power
than you realize.
Start talking
and you can name your terms,
get immunity, protection.
Otherwise, I'm afraid
the next time I see you,
you'll be in a body bag.
- She has him.
- You putting money on that?
Hell no. I didn't say she could land him.
You said I was free to go,
so I'm gonna go.
Okay, wait.
This offer's got a clock on it,
like your life.
Here's my card. Call me anytime.
So much room for improvement,
Miss Cleo.
Yeah, I know.
I didn't have anything to hold him on.
To be fair, you got him to the finish line.
Yeah, but I didn't get him across.
So what now?
Write it up and hand it off to Narcotics.
This one goes in your loss column.
Where have you been?
Buying a new phone.
Why? What's wrong?
The florist tried
calling you, like, ten times.
He thought we'd ghosted him.
He had another order
and he sold our flowers.
What? Why wouldn't he call you?
I might have been on another call.
Okay, let's just focus on solutions.
Well, there are none. It's end of day.
There is no florist
that could handle an order
this large last-minute.
But we need to have flowers
for the wedding.
We will, and I know
exactly where to get them.
Don't worry about this.
You just go and enjoy girls' night.
- I got this.
- Okay. Thank you.
Where's my ring?
Hey, what's up?
My wedding ring is missing.
No, it's not.
Randy got caramel on it,
so I got it cleaned for you.
- Here it is. Here it is.
- Thank you.
Knock, knock.
I have a cake
for the Nolan-Nune wedding.
I'm sorry, but there's been a mistake,
which is clearly
our official wedding motto.
This cake is supposed to be delivered
to our wedding tomorrow.
We're closed tomorrow. It's now or never.
No one ever mentioned that
to me when I placed the order.
How am I supposed to move this c
wait, that's wrong.
- Is that coconut cream?
- Yeah, vegan.
No. Deadly.
My husband is allergic to that.
- You're gonna have to redo it.
- Closed tomorrow.
Your husband doesn't have to eat it.
It's our wedding cake.
Hey. Hey.
It's gonna be okay. It's gonna be okay.
Can you help me make
a new wedding cake?
No. God no.
I burn kitchens down.
But we can call in for reinforcements.
Hey, Randy.
I know I said I didn't want
a bachelor party,
but I need you to help me
get some guys together.
These are perfect!
This is a delightful bachelor party.
Not a bachelor party.
Hello.
Please do not be using
the masking tape.
We have this entzueckend floral tape.
Yeah, Randy watched
about 57 ClipTalk videos,
so he's the expert now.
Wesley was catching me up
on your lawsuit.
Yeah, I'm trying not to think about it.
The suit's frivolous. Judge will see that.
I'm not worried about the lawsuit.
I'm worried about Monica.
Oscar can't afford
15 minutes of her time,
much less full representation.
Elijah has to be bankrolling this.
Maybe, but Monica has plenty
other clients that hate the LAPD.
Whatever happens, maybe we just don't
talk about it at the wedding.
I'll tell Bailey later.
The timing couldn't be worse.
Leave it to Oscar to sue Nolan
the day before his wedding.
Wait, Oscar is suing John?
Please tell me your bachelorette party
will involve less baking
and more actual party.
That is a long way off,
if it's even in our future.
You and Tim are so great together.
We're great when she's not accusing me
of made-up transgressions.
Look, I'm not imagining things.
Tim is traumatized
by what happened with Isabel.
He just won't admit it.
Honestly, I think she's projecting
or just using this as an excuse.
Yeah, well, undercover work is
kind of scary and dangerous.
Maybe he's not the only one
that's scared of what might happen.
No. I'm fine.
He has the problem.
How do I prove that I'm not the problem?
I have an idea.
It's only ein wenig crazy.
Hey.
Hey, I gotta get out of here. This is sad.
We can get dinner
at that Korean place you like.
I can't. Look, I failed
with a drug mule today.
I really need to show Harper
what I'm capable of.
- What, by baking a cake?
- Whatever it takes.
See you tomorrow.
- That was Aaron.
- Yeah, I figured.
You guys are close nowadays.
Yeah.
Is that a problem?
It could be.
Look, you guys went
through a trauma together,
and it bonded you,
and that connection makes
every other relationship pale
in comparison.
But you cannot be
his entire support system.
Okay? That is a slow poison.
Okay. Yeah, I'll meet you there.
Tim wants me to meet him at the station.
Maybe he's ready to make up.
Or he has something to say
that's gonna make you
want to kill him, and he wants witnesses.
Man, if he wants to keep arguing,
I don't see the point.
Okay, the cake is almost done.
We just need to do the fondant flowers.
There's four different types,
and we need 20 of each.
Run.
Hey. Do you know where Tim is?
Yeah. I think he's in interrogation.
What?
What is happening right now?
I am gonna prove to you
that I'm rooting for you.
With a lie detector test?
- Yes.
- Wait, so I can ask anything?
Well, I mean, the point is
for you to ask me
about you making detective, you know,
working undercover, that sort of thing.
Sure.
But, I mean, you did go through
all this trouble, right?
We should be thorough, don't you think?
What do you want to ask?
When I have you trap bugs
in my apartment,
do you release them outside like I ask?
No.
True? I knew it. You just kill them?
Yes. Because they're bugs.
Okay.
Do you love me?
Yes.
I love you.
True.
Okay.
You ready?
- Big one.
- Ready.
Do you want me to be
an undercover detective?
Yes.
You liar.
I guess we really do have a problem.
Today is the day.
It is.
It's gonna be great.
As long as we're married at the end of it,
I'll be happy.
Why do you taste like frosting?
New face serum.
That's nice.
This is nice.
Let's just snuggle in peace
for a little while longer.
Okay.
And the moment is over.
Next time we get married,
no houseguests.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Where's Henry?
He was supposed to get in last night.
Landing at Andrews, I think.
Why would he be landing
at an air force base?
Did I forget to mention
that he had some travel complications?
Yes, you did.
Same way you forgot to mention
that Oscar is suing you
and that's why you had
to give up your phone yesterday.
Touché. I didn't want to worry you.
Exactly.
Henry should make it in time
for the ceremony, though.
Well, that's all that matters.
- Let's go get married.
- Let's do it.
You look amazing.
I mean, the one-shoulder was great too,
but this is my favorite.
Thank you. I was torn.
The other one had a beautiful color,
but it did not go with the shoes.
And if you swap out the shoes,
then the handbag doesn't work.
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
So I went with a suit.
Hey, me too.
Mine has a tie.
My God, same.
So how long did you stay?
I bailed right after we talked.
You know, it doesn't seem
like you're hanging out
with the other guys much.
I guess not.
I'd rather hang out with you.
Yeah, but it can't hurt, though,
having more people to talk to,
plus your shrink.
What, you trying to get rid of me?
Never. Never.
Just... just looking out for you.
Thanks.
You're the best.
By the way, I read
your book club selection.
When Elsie died in childbirth,
I must admit, I cried.
Me too. That was awful.
And when it turned out
that the doctor's mother
was alive the whole time...
Well, that I saw coming.
None of that happened
in the book, did it?
No. What's going on?
After everything
that happened with Aaron,
I saw how much good I could do
working in the hospital.
So I decided to finish
my social work degree.
That's where I've been going at night.
Why the subterfuge?
I was worried I'd get three classes in
and realize I couldn't hack it.
Going back after all
these years, it was scary.
I did not want to have to worry
about disappointing you.
As if you could.
Okay, so how are you doing?
Top of my class.
Graduate next week.
Hospital job starts the week after.
I was gonna tell you this weekend.
- You go, girl.
- I was gonna...
That's good.
Pardon me one second.
Small problem.
Father O'Malley's stuck in traffic.
Okay. Should we wait?
He's in Chatsworth.
So no. Okay.
Sorry, everyone, if I could just get
your attention for one minute.
I realize this is literally last-minute.
Is anyone here qualified
to officiate a wedding?
I can.
As a minister
of the Universal Life Church,
I would be honored
to marry you two crazy kids.
- Sit down, German.
- Okay.
- I got this.
- Thank you.
Here, I'll take that.
Please be seated.
You are all here today
because you love these two.
They're here to make
a commitment under God
in front of family and friends
to love, honor, and cherish each other
for the rest of their lives.
Bailey.
I'm suddenly so nervous.
There is nothing,
literally nothing else in my life
I am as certain of as marrying you.
I must have written
a hundred different vows
and I threw them all away
'cause there were too many words.
And the way you make me feel
is so simple to express.
I feel loved and seen
and desired and happy.
For that, I will love you forever and a day.
That's your ring.
- My turn.
- Yes.
Bailey Nune,
you came into my life
in a towel on my doorstep
with an unlikely story
about being locked out
by a meddlesome dog.
And I remember thinking,
"I'm either being conned by a hot model,
or I have just met
the woman of my dreams."
You're damn right I love and cherish you.
You are the most impressive
person I've ever met.
And I wake up every morning
to the dream of being your man.
And I promise that making you happy
will be my everyday everything.
Well, there's nothing
I can say to top that,
so I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
Kiss your bride.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Mrs. and Mr. John Nolan.
- Hey, Randy.
- James.
What a lucky man to be married
to the beautiful and terrifying
Detective Harper.
I couldn't agree more.
Hey, I was wondering
if I could share a playlist.
What, to...
So, what, you just had
this playlist ready to go?
I set it up the minute that you mentioned
Randy was the DJ.
- That's why I love you.
- I got your back.
Tim and Lucy are gonna be okay?
I'm sure they'll work it out.
- You want to get some air?
- Yeah, sure.
Okay.
You know Mercury is merging
into Pisces right now,
which tends to amplify psychic activity,
especially for people born
with Mercury in Pisces.
And that means?
Just pay attention to your dreams
for the next couple of weeks.
The cosmos might be trying
to tell you something.
Yeah, well, my dreams
are mainly, um... violent.
Yeah. Yeah, me too.
Yeah, I haven't told anyone that.
Not even the shrink.
Okay, isn't that exactly the kind of stuff
you're supposed to be telling her?
If I'm trying to get better, yes.
If I'm trying to get back on patrol, no.
I mean, you're the only person
that I can talk to about all this.
And I will always be here for you.
Aaron.
I...
No, I thought
- I'm sorry.
- No, it's okay.
- I'm so... I am so sorry.
- It's fine.
I just... I just don't
yeah, well, I'm gonna go grab a drink.
- Yeah.
No.
Hello?
Hey, it's Seth.
Flower pot heroin guy. Allegedly.
- You were right... I need help.
- They're hunting for me.
Send me your address.
I'll come pick you up.
Tequila shots. Keep 'em coming.
Clearly, I'm more conflicted
about you working undercover
than I realized.
It's understandable.
Losing Isabel in such a horrible way,
I mean, how could you
possibly be over that?
Yeah, but it's unfair to you.
I need to deal with it.
You know, your dream
should have nothing
to do with my issues.
Thank you.
We're gonna get through this.
I love you.
Well, you say that, but till I put you
under a lie detector, how can I be sure?
No, not a chance.
I'm not doing it.
You guys made up. Awesome.
- Yeah.
- Everyone was so worried.
They were like... I told them, "It's fine."
"They're solid," so...
Whoa, how much have you had to drink?
I don't know. Who cares?
Well, you should, because as cops,
we're always
one person's bad choice away
from being on duty.
Hey, where... where's Celina?
I don't know. Why would I know?
It's not like we're together, so
yeah, all right.
See ya.
Come on!
No, no! All right, all right.
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on.
- Celina?
- Hey, I'm in trouble.
Gallegos called me.
He called me...
Celina's in trouble.
She went to meet a CI.
- Where?
- I don't know.
Call was cut off. I'm waiting
on a warrant for her phone.
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
Something with Celina.
This is Grey.
I have an officer in distress.
I need a dedicated airship
and citywide alert pending location.
I'll get Metro on standby.
- We gotta get changed.
- Give me your keys.
I'll grab your go bags out of your cars.
- Thank you.
- I'll go with you. Come on.
All right, Celina is downtown.
They're waiting
on a more precise location.
We'll get it on our way.
- I am sorry, I have to go.
- I know. I know.
Just please don't die
on our wedding night.
Hey, I heard
something happened to Celina.
- Is she okay?
- We don't know.
We're going downtown to find her.
Okay, I'm coming with you.
No, you're drunk and not
cleared for active duty.
Sit your ass down and do some praying.
We got him.
Hey, handsome.
Hey, let's get some coffee in you, yeah?
Yeah.
She's not here.
Start a grid search.
Whittier to 1st to the 10.
They took her by car.
She could be anywhere right now.
Guys, I got some blood over here.
Looks like somebody got
dragged that way.
Two male suspects. One gun visible.
We gotta get past 'em to get inside.
Get it done.
Harper, Lopez,
we'll breach from the back.
All right, how do you want to play this?
Take off your tie.
Right here. Down on your knees.
Here. I'll stay with them.
You guys go.
Last chance... tell me where my stuff is,
or I will cut your throat
and move on to your girlfriend.
All right, it's a tactical nightmare in there.
There's no way to get
in there quickly enough
to neutralize them and save Celina.
What the...
Sarge.
Give me his jacket.
- Time's up.
- Hey, hey. Come on.
Aah!
Hey! Hey!
Put your hands in the air!
- Police, hands up!
- Police!
Police! Show me your hands!
Show me your hands!
Not to judge,
I think you would have had
more fun at the wedding.
No kidding.
Bailey?
How's it going?
I can't move my body.
Did I finish packing for our honeymoon?
Yeah, almost.
I say we buy clothes there.
That is genius.
I mean, what do we need anyway?
- Just bathing suits.
- Yeah.
Wow.
I'm so sorry I bailed on the wedding.
You didn't miss much.
The cake was kind of a disaster.
How much longer before
we have to be at the airport?
Four hours.
There's plenty of time for a little nap.
Siri, wake me in an hour.
Yeah.
I didn't get that. Could you try again?
Damn it.