Celina, look out!
Officer down.
Help him.
Tell me what you're feeling.
Frustration.
But not fear?
No.
Today was the first
time during this exercise
that your heart rate didn't spike.
You remained calm.
Why do you think that is?
Because I know
there's no way I could have
stopped what happened.
That's right. The men
who ambushed you
and officer juarez rigged the game.
No matter which way you
turned, whether you split up
or stayed together,
even if you called it in,
none of that would
have made a difference
because they were ready.
One of you was gonna
be shot that night.
And who knows?
If you hadn't made the decisions you did,
maybe it would have
been celina, instead of you.
No, you're... you're right.
Um, I've been blaming myself.
Like, if I had been smarter,
I could have somehow avoided it.
But it was out of my control.
Congratulations, officer thorsen.
In my professional opinion,
you are ready to return to active duty.
I'm just really excited to get back to work.
- Yeah.
Look, I told you I'm fine.
I'll just retake the
detective's exam in two years.
It's not a big deal.
You know, every time a woman in my life
has said she was fine,
she most definitely was not.
I'm not gonna pretend like I
wasn't a little disappointed.
But I've made my peace with it.
Plus, I'm a professional.
- Unless you want me to be upset.
- No, of course not.
Hey, Lucy, I heard
about the detective exam.
- Tough break.
- Yes, thank you.
I'm fine.
Whenever Bailey
says she's fine like that,
I up my life insurance.
There he is.
Everyone drive safe out there.
Thorsen is back in the shop.
As always, detective,
your unwavering support
means the world to me.
Don't fret.
In Harper speak, that's
practically an "I love you."
Bradford, got a minute?
Congrats on being cleared.
- Thanks.
- So any nerves?
Not really.
Um, I feel strong in
mind, body, and spirit.
- I'm ready.
- Thorsen's not ready.
What's the first thing an officer returning
from injury worries about?
Gettin' hurt again.
Especially after a
near-fatal like thorsen's.
You afraid he's gonna go
turtle up when things get real?
I don't wanna wait to find out.
In this business, we don't
have the luxury of do-overs.
So you want me to take him out today
to get punched in the face.
Officially, I want you
to supervise his ability
to cope with stress,
both mental and physical.
You got it.
Let's see how he does against the train.
Thorsen, you're with me.
Metro needs a support officer.
Oh, um, yes, sir.
Ooh.
You know what it means
to "turtle up," thorsen?
I don't think so, sir.
It happens when an officer returns
to the job after a trauma,
put under some kind of pressure,
usually physical, for the first time.
Instead of falling back on their training,
they shrink into a shell,
where they feel safe.
So you think I'm gonna turtle up?
Maybe.
If you do, there are lots
of companies looking
for delivery guys with
a good driving record.
Well, actually, my
fallback career is gonna be
influencer/shoe designer.
But I-I see what you're saying.
So that's why I'm riding with you.
So I gotta pass, what, some
type of Tim test so I don't...
It's called the train.
Stands for tactical, responsive, assertive,
investigative, and nerve.
And I'm gonna test you
on all five major functions
in stress environments.
Evaluate, improvise,
adapt, and overcome.
You ready for this?
Bring it on.
So how did you like riding
with sergeant Bradford?
It was very educational.
Both he and detective Harper
have very distinctive styles.
Dispatch, you said the rp was
on the south side of the park?
Affirmative, 7-Adam-15.
Okay, so did they, like,
say anything about me?
They did.
Like all rookies, you
are a work in progress.
Over here!
Hi, I'm officer Nolan.
This is officer juarez.
You called about a body?
Yeah, it's, in there.
Um, someone jammed the lock,
but when I finally got it open, she...
She was just lying there
it's okay. It's okay. Stay here.
We're gonna need to get some
information from you, okay?
Okay?
- After you.
- Yep.
Overdose?
No.
Lividity in the cheeks.
She died facedown and was moved here.
Looks like a homicide. Let's call it in.
Control, requesting detectives
for a possible homicide.
Welcome to your first test.
Let me guess... that's
the stress environment?
It's a little more than that.
Man inside is Tyson
kalashnikov, 6'4", 275.
Has a warrant for a
missed court appearance.
Last time he was arrested,
he broke the cop's nose.
I assume calling for backup is cheating?
Train's leaving, officer thorsen.
Okay, let's do this.
Police! Open up!
It's open.
Clear!
Tyson, show yourself!
Could one of you get me a beer?
I moved the picnic blanket
so we could examine her head.
She was definitely moved postmortem.
Obvious blunt force trauma to the head.
What's this under her shirt?
What is that?
It's the signature of the pentagram killer.
Pardon us just one moment.
So the pentagram killer is wanted
in connection to a string
of unsolved homicides
in the early 2000s.
His victims were all
middle-aged females.
He'd carve a pentagram
into their midsections
after he killed them.
Then in 2009, he just stopped.
Hulu just dropped a docuseries on him.
Maybe the renewed
notoriety inspired him
to come out of retirement.
The hysteria was real.
I was away at college,
and I made my brothers
escort my mom everywhere.
Scary that they never caught the guy.
Well, the city threw
everything they had at it,
multiple agencies working 24/7.
My first sergeant was on the task force.
Speaking of, whenever we respond
to a potentially high-profile event,
it's important to notify
the watch commander.
Yes, sir.
Adam-200, be advised, our
db might be a possible victim
of the pentagram killer.
Officer juarez!
Did I do something wrong?
As her to, that is on you.
Yes, ma'am. I am sorry, ma'am.
Officer Suarez, I should
have been clearer.
You never give out that
kind of sensitive information
over the radio.
Now every news organization or hobbyist
with a scanner has it.
- My god.
- I didn't think that
did I hear someone say
"pentagram killer" on the radio?
- Um...
- I'm... I'm so sorry.
Is that really bad?
Cases like this capture
the public's attention.
People call in with tips,
trying to be a part of it.
But most of them are a
complete waste of time.
Yeah, because when people panic,
they call 911 at every bump in the night.
So no, that... that was not ideal.
Okay, is there anything I can do to help?
Just take the witness back to the station,
and maybe stay off the radio.
Yes, ma'am. We're on it.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
You want me to start canvassing?
No, we need to secure
the perimeter first.
Um, there's no one
watching the northwest corner.
Probably because it's
where the hell dumpsters are.
Yeah, of course. Whatever you need.
As a patrol officer, I'm here
to support your investigation
- in any way that I can.
- Great.
We're gonna head back to the station
and dig into this case file
and let crime scene do their thing.
Come here.
Got it?
Yo, just lean him up against the car.
Control, Bradford, can I get a
transport Van to our location?
What's that?
No idea.
I'll check it out.
Tyson?
Tyson? It's me.
Hi.
You looking for Tyson?
- Have you heard the good news?
- What good news?
Our lord and savior has
come to save our souls.
Well, amen, sister.
- Ha.
- Can I see some ID?
Ma'am?
Excuse me. Ma'am.
No!
Hey, Harper, I just found a pile of vomit
on the far northwest corner of the park.
Lucky you.
It's unlikely to be related,
but we still need to collect it, just in case.
I will have tid process it
as soon as they're done with the scene.
Oh, um, how long do
you think that'll take?
A couple hours, four tops.
In the meantime, keep an eye on it.
It's my lucky... it's my lucky day.
- I wouldn't want to be her.
- Ooh.
Man, that man is an olympic-level yeller.
You got an ID on our Vic?
Yeah, Cheryl budny, 42,
works at Lincoln junior high.
She left at her usual
time around 5:00 P.M
didn't show up today.
She live close by the park?
No, culver city.
So that means that the dump site
is most likely related to the killer.
Yeah, Cheryl's brother
lives over in little Armenia.
He should be here any minute.
I reserved interview three for us.
Great.
You still have all your fingers and toes?
Sergeant grey was very fair.
And again, I'm... I'm very sorry.
Don't worry about us.
It's you guys who are
gonna pay the price.
What do you mean?
Any more evidence pointing
to the pentagram killer?
Some of the signature qualities match
his previous victims, but
all are public knowledge.
Which means we can't
decisively say it's him.
Nolan, I need you guys 10-8.
Calls are backing up.
26 pending related to the pentagram.
And that's the price.
Cheryl's next of kin is on his way.
Call us if you get anything interesting.
Phone call. On the phone.
All right, what have
we got, officer thorsen?
Well, she attempted to contact
a well-known criminal and one suspect.
She ran when she saw
my uniform, giving me
probable cause to believe
that she also was engaged
in criminal activity.
And she also held $15,000 in cash.
And cash is frequently used
to finance and conceal criminal activity.
Not bad.
Is that enough to arrest?
I mean, she tried to scratch my face off.
So there's a 1-48 right there.
But I'm actually more interested
in why she had all that money on her.
Good. Under stress,
you made a tactical entry.
You were responsive to criminal activity
and assertive when she tried to run.
You may build this train just yet.
Well, what about "nerve"?
I mean, she hit me with her bag,
and did you see her nails?
Nope.
Hurry up and process 'em.
We got work to do.
Jeff budny?
I'm detective Lopez.
This is detective Harper.
If you follow us, we have a room set up.
I got 30 minutes left on my lunch break.
Can't you just say whatever it
is you need to say right here?
Well, we're sorry to have to tell you this,
but it's about your sister, Cheryl.
What about her?
She's deceased.
What?
What happened?
It was a homicide.
- I'm so sorry.
- A homicide?
Wait, wait, wait.
That's... when? How?
Listen, I know this is difficult,
but we really would like to
speak with you somewhere
where there's more privacy.
Just tell me what happened to my sister.
They discovered her
body in a park this morning.
And that's really all we can say right now.
That's all you can say?
Did you two get along?
I mean, when was the last
time you saw or spoke with her?
We were tight, all right? I don't know.
I talked to her a couple days ago.
Wednesday, maybe. I don't know.
Can you think of anyone
who wanted to harm her?
No.
She worked at a grade school.
Well, I'm sorry, but I have to ask,
what were you doing last night?
You mean while my
sister was being murdered?
Yeah, watching the
laker game at Barney's.
20 people can vouch for me.
Listen, I know you're upset,
and I cannot even imagine
what you are going through right now.
But the more you give us,
the faster we can find who did this.
I can't do this right now, okay?
There's people I need to call.
My mom, jeez. I gotta call my mom.
We understand, but as soon as possible,
we need to sit down with
you and get a full statement.
Call us when you're ready.
Any time, day or night.
Well, he seems genuinely upset.
Yeah, still gonna check that alibi, though.
Damn straight.
All right, sarge, both
suspects are booked.
Do you want a medal?
No, sir.
I just really would like to figure out
what a suburban housewife
was doing with all that cash.
And why bring it to Tyson?
Opioids, gambling, debt, pirated movies.
Who knows? Who cares?
They never completed the transaction.
If there's more to it,
shouldn't we dig a little deeper?
Good.
The I in train stands
for investigative initiative.
That's two I's.
Never mind.
You don't get the I
unless it's under stress.
So we're gonna make this interesting.
You've got nine minutes
to get to the bottom of this.
If you can't, I'm gonna
recommend we extend
your probation and return
you to the fto program.
Nine minutes? Why not ten?
Now it's eight minutes, 47 seconds.
Ticktock.
So why were you attempting
to pay Tyson kalashnikov
$15,000 in cash?
'Cause he's my gigolo.
I got a thing for guys
who can't move their arms.
Hello?
Yes, arm casts. Very sexy.
Your husband's in prison.
I mean, your husband is Austin Walker,
doing three to five in San Quentin
for embezzlement.
- Is that right?
- Austin made a mistake.
Yeah, one with very
serious consequences.
Now, did you know
that Tyson did four
stints in San Quentin?
And that's where he's
heading back to now.
And it looks like he's also the lieutenant
of the devil's crown prison gang.
They run your husband's prison.
Okay, so connecting those dots,
I'm guessing that you paid Tyson
to keep your husband
safe while he's inside.
Is that what's happening?
Tyson said that if I didn't pay
him the money by tomorrow,
Austin was as good as dead.
He's all I have. I didn't have a choice.
I didn't... I didn't know what else to do.
Okay, look, don't worry.
All right? I'm gonna help you.
Sir, I need to call the prison
and have Austin Walker put
into protective custody, like, right now.
Already done, and you
still have 25 seconds.
Are you sure your
investigation is complete?
Yeah, I think so.
I mean, it's just a
classic protection racket.
Are you asking me,
or are you telling me?
No, I'm telling... I'm telling you.
Okay.
Unless I'm missing something.
I didn't say that.
Time's up.
Ooh, listen to this one.
A man says that his neighbor's cat
is possessed by the pentagram.
There's gotta be one tip on that call line
that is not totally insane.
Let's see.
A lady with a devil-worshipping nephew.
- Skip it.
- Teenage girl thought
that her mailman was the pentagram
and was there to snatch her.
She actually sprayed him with a hose.
- Next.
- Old lady claims her husband
committed the murders
while he was on shore leave.
Was he in the Navy?
It looks like commercial fisherman.
- Attach us to that.
- Really?
Commercial fisherman work a lot at night
perfect excuse to be out late, hunting.
All of our victims had ligature
marks from being tied up.
You know who's really
good at tying knots?
- Fishermen?
- Bingo.
Mrs. Opal Jesper?
We're here about a tip you called in.
I'm... I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done
that. It was a mistake.
Ma'am...
You said your husband
is the pentagram killer.
That does not sound like a mistake.
I didn't know what to do.
I found this.
Sandra Owens.
That's the first victim.
Ma'am, where is your
husband right now?
He's been dead for seven years.
Probably more inside.
Thanks very much.
Thanks.
What's gonna happen to me?
Well, the detectives are gonna have
a few more questions
for you back at the station.
At the station?
- Will you be there?
- No, ma'am.
I'm a patrol officer, not an investigator.
Um, I'll tell you what.
Why don't you take my card?
If you need anything, give me a call.
My mobile number's on there, all right?
If you'll excuse us just for a moment?
Thanks.
Hey.
That widow looks like
she's sweet on you.
Yeah, Nolan gave her his number.
Yes, I was trying to build rapport.
- Did it work?
- Hard to say.
She insists she didn't know
anything about the murders
until after her husband died
and she found the trophies.
I mean, how could she not have known?
Well, her husband wasn't
on the original suspect list,
which means that he was
good at flying under the radar.
Well, at least we can
eliminate the pentagram killer
as a suspect in Cheryl budny's case.
Let's hope his copycat isn't as skilled
at covering his tracks.
Nolan, juarez.
So I understand you took the call.
Yes, sir. We got lucky.
Well, actually, officer Nolan picked it out.
- He thought it sounded credible.
- Nice catch.
Look, the mayor asked me
to give a press conference
announcing the identity
of the pentagram killer.
I'd like you two to be there
so I can recognize your work.
Yes, sir. Thank you, sir.
All right, go get cleaned
up. You're gonna be on TV.
Do you think I have time for a blowout?
Absolutely not.
- No?
- Come on.
You ready?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Is that the widow?
It must be.
You know, I almost attached to that call.
But I got pulled to a 2-11 that
turned out to be a false alarm.
Then you'd be the one on TV,
and primm would have realized
what a giant mistake he made
torpedoing your detective's exam.
Yeah, something like that.
Instead, I spent the day
breathing in hot dumpster fumes
while standing guard over a pile of puke
for three hours on the off chance
it belonged to our killer.
- Did it?
- Nope.
It was a sick dog.
Okay, so you had a crappy day.
You've had 'em before,
and you'll have 'em again.
The best part about being on patrol is
you never know what's gonna happen.
Maybe tomorrow, you'll be the big hero.
I would just settle for not having to deal
with any bodily fluids.
Yeah, don't be too greedy.
So do you really believe
the widow had no idea?
I don't know. I mean, there was a time
when I couldn't have
conceived of not being able to tell
that my partner was keeping
something from me, but
then I went and hid a
whole husband from you.
Yeah, pretty much. But you know what?
Getting through that made us stronger.
- Yeah.
- What about you?
Do you think if you
found out I was a murderer
would you turn me in?
Absolutely.
Not a moment's hesitation.
I think you should be more
worried if I did hesitate.
- Yeah.
- What about you?
Well, as a cop, it'd be
my duty to arrest you.
But I have to say, I would be pretty handy
at helping you hide a body.
So romantic.
I know, right?
Hey.
How'd today go?
Good, I think.
Sergeant Bradford said
something to me today
that made me think I need
to dig deeper on our case,
but you ever read something ten times
and still feel like you're
missing the point of it?
Performing under
pressure takes many forms.
Sometimes physical,
so you feel nervous.
Other times, mental.
And you just can't see
the forest from the trees.
Yeah, well, all I can see is trees.
So any advice?
Yeah, stop thinking about it.
Take a walk.
Take a shower.
Turn your brain off.
Let your mind find the answer.
In other words, go home.
Yes, sir.
Sleep couldn't hurt.
That's right.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Hey, did you come over
here just to check on me,
or did you need something?
It can keep till the morning.
I mean, I'm here now. What's up?
I just received a call
from San Quentin prison.
And apparently they
failed to grasp the urgency
of your request to put Austin Walker
into protective custody.
When they finally went to move him,
he was already dead.
Sorry, son.
That sounds like quite the first day back.
It was.
I mean, in some ways, I
feel really good about it.
You know, I didn't freeze,
and I handled every crazy
obstacle Tim threw at me.
But for the day to end like that...
When your watch commander told you
that man had been killed,
- how did you feel?
- Frustrated.
You realize that's the
exact word you used
yesterday after our
visualization exercise?
Well, it's frustrating, you know,
knowing I can be doing everything right
and things still go wrong.
Lack of control is scary,
especially when your job
involves so much violence.
Hey, when you start
to notice those feelings,
try focusing on the
things you can control.
Tyson is still in custody, and I can work
on connecting him to the murder,
but what I still don't get is,
if Stacy had until today to
pay the protection money,
why was her husband
murdered last night?
I did miss something.
So our victim had lots of enemies.
At first, Cheryl's neighbors
and coworkers were
a little hesitant to
speak ill of the dead, but
yeah, but once they got
going, they would not stop.
They would not stop.
That tracks with what we found online.
Her school's unofficial message
board has an entire subgroup
devoted to hating on her.
The most extreme
comments coming from a user
going by the handle grid iron gangsta.
We traced the account back
to this guy, Conrad bataglia.
No criminal history, but he
lives with his wife, justine,
a mile away from the park,
and he coaches football
at Cheryl's school.
So he's a gridiron something.
Let me give you a few highlights.
Um, "she deserves cancer."
"I fantasize about shoving
a stapler down her throat."
And "someone should
euthanize the bitch."
Yikes.
Yeah, so bring Conrad in.
People find it easier to
lie to officers in uniform,
so lock him into a statement
and pretend like you
believe everything he says.
In the meantime, we'll blow up
all his possible defenses and alibis.
You want us to mayberry it?
Not full-on Barney fife,
but don't let him know he's a suspect.
Roger.
Who's Barney fife?
Okay, every time you ask
me a question like that...
All I hear is, "you're old."
- Okay, I'm sorry, sir.
- No, but really, who is he?
- Hello?
- Officer Nolan?
- It's opal Jesper.
- Hi, Mrs. Jesper.
Can you tell the reporters
outside my house to leave?
No, I really can't.
But if they're trespassing, just call 911.
I have no privacy!
The police took my front door.
They probably thought there
was potential evidence on it.
- Well, that's ridiculous!
- What could they find?
Mrs. Jesper, look,
any questions about the investigation
should really be directed
to detective Harper
or detective Lopez.
Meanwhile, I advise you
stay with friends or relatives
until things settle down a little bit.
And now I hate to do
this, but I have to go.
I'm gonna rush you off, okay? All right?
- All right.
- Thank you.
Okay, let's go... where are we going?
Nolan, look.
Hello?
Mr. Bataglia?
Police!
Hello?
Control, 7-Adam-15.
We have an open door.
We're making entry to
the residence to clear it.
Mr. Bataglia!
Police department!
We're coming inside your house!
Go.
Clear!
Juarez!
The rest of the house is clear.
No sign of bataglia.
7-Adam-15, we have
a db at the residence.
Notify homicide, watch commander,
and issue a bolo for Conrad bataglia.
Thanks for coming back, Mrs. Walker,
but I just need a little more information
before I can charge anyone.
- Anything to help my husband.
- Okay.
Now, we're hoping to identify some
of Mr. Kalashnikov's associates.
I mean, he couldn't have
been conducting business
all by himself with both arms in a cast.
Um, during your dealings with him,
did you ever see any of these men?
Um... Him.
Yeah, it's him.
I-I-I-I think I've seen him before.
He's involved, and he scares me.
- Are you sure?
- I'm positive.
Listen, can you tell me what is going on?
I've called the prison multiple times.
No one will tell me anything about Austin.
I'm getting worried here.
Your husband's in isolation,
where no one can get to him.
They're moving him to a
different facility tomorrow,
where he'll be safe.
What a relief.
What a relief. Thank you, officers.
My god, thank you.
Hello?
- Austin's alive!
- What?
They have him in isolation
so no one can get to him.
They're gonna move him tomorrow.
What the hell are you gonna do now?
- Hi.
- Stacy?
- Give me the phone.
- Wh... excuse me?
Stacy, are you there?
This is sergeant Bradford with the LAPD.
This whole conversation
is being recorded.
You want to save me some
time and tell me your name,
or are you gonna make me run a trace?
Wrong number.
Trace it is.
I don't... I don't understand
what's happening right now.
You're under arrest
for the murder for hire
of your husband.
- I don't understand.
- Look, we lied.
And I'm sorry to inform
you, your husband is dead.
He was killed last night in jail
by one of Tyson's cronies.
And, look, I couldn't see why you wanted
your husband dead until
I read his criminal history.
Again, no convictions,
but multiple phone calls
to your house for domestic violence.
Throw in a mistress
and a judge authorized
a tap on your phone.
And you just confirmed our suspicions.
Okay.
My goodness.
Judge just signed the
ramey warrant for Conrad.
Bolo's in the system.
Yeah, and we put his car in svs.
How was the wife found?
Kitchen floor, facing the west wall.
Multiple stab wounds,
weapon still outstanding.
Well, then what, wife
finds out hubby kills Cheryl
and then confronts him?
Hubby panics and kills
the wife to silence her.
He realizes what he's
done and goes on the run.
Desperate idiot's playbook.
There are no clear prints on
the doorknob, just smudges.
What's the time element
for when she died?
Go ahead. You got this.
Well, I mean, a body loses heat
at a rate of 1.5 degrees per hour.
Thermostat is at 68.
But the body of the victim wasn't
that cold when we found it.
So I would say about
an hour, 90 minutes tops.
She's right.
What about the canvass?
Not home, not home, all not home.
Home, but didn't see or hear anything.
Harper searched Conrad's social media
and emergency contacts.
And if Conrad is running,
he's gonna need help.
So here are his closest friends.
Start from the bottom
and work your way up.
All right, I'll get chen's help with this.
She'll take odds, we'll take evens.
Great.
Control, location nine is unoccupied.
Show me en route to
location number seven.
All right, location six, Jose Martinez,
his husband, Todd.
It should be right up
there... By that Toyota.
Did you see that?
Yeah, I saw bushes
move. Is that Conrad?
Control, we have a possible
at location six on brywood.
Adam-19 attach.
Conrad, I wanna see your hands.
7-Adam-15, code-6 on suspect bataglia,
2300 block brywood.
Don't move. Show me your hands!
We got a foot pursuit,
northbound brywood!
Come here. Get up.
- No, wait!
- Against the car!
Aah. No! Wait!
You don't understand!
He's trying to kill me!
Hands. Hands!
Are you hurt anywhere else?
Just my head and right here.
All right, take us through
what happened, slowly.
This man broke into
our house and tied us up.
And he made me watch while he killed
while he killed justine.
I don't know how I got away,
but I must have broke the restraints.
He tried to stop me,
but I got away, and I-I just kept running.
He's almost ready for transport.
11-79 was just reported
at 1025 south butter field drive.
That's opal's address.
Control, 7-Adam-15, you have
any more details on the 11-79?
There's a man trapped under
the homeowner's vehicle.
Fire and ra already en route.
Control, attach us to this.
Chen?
Yeah, what's up?
Would you escort
Conrad to the hospital?
- He's been mirandized.
- Yeah, of course.
Come on.
What just happened?
Something about the pentagram widow.
He'll be ready to go in five.
Are they looking for him?
The guy who killed my wife?
- Can you describe him?
- I don't know.
He was white, average
height, average weight.
He was... he was deranged.
Any idea why he targeted you?
Okay, look, I want to get this guy.
All right? Your wife deserves justice.
But white, average height, weight,
that's not gonna get him.
Does this have anything
to do with Cheryl budny?
Look, I-I didn't mean to kill her.
I was just so tired of her lies.
We were fighting, and I shoved her.
And I guess she hit her head.
All right, well, killing her
might have been an accident,
but carving a pentagram
into her stomach was not.
Why didn't you call the police?
I don't know. I-I-I was scared.
I-I-I knew you guys would see
the post that I made about her.
So I tried to make it look
like it was that pentagram guy
from the documentary.
But then today, I got a
text from Cheryl, and it said
that she wanted me to feel
the same pain that I caused.
It's on my phone. Look.
Aah!
Officers taking fire,
2300 block of brywood.
Shooter has a long gun.
23-31, we're 10-9-7 on brywood.
Go.
Ready?
I'm clear!
Go!
Nobody else down brywood!
He's got a clear shot.
Stay off brywood.
Anybody hurt?
We're okay.
Conrad's dead.
Medic took a shot in the leg.
- We can't let him escape.
- We gotta seal him off.
We can't get a unit behind him.
There's a fence. The
alley doesn't go through.
- Can't they just climb over?
- Shooter will pick 'em off
as soon as they climb up.
Can I get an airship to help
seal off brywood to the south?
Copy. Air 11 is en route.
Eta, less than three minutes.
He's gonna be gone by then.
I can get down the
alleyway and just cut him off.
No, way, that's a 40-yard open-field run.
Well, if his head pops up, just blow it off.
I'll be all right.
Just let me know when you're ready.
Come on.
Go.
She made it. Code-4.
And she doesn't want
to give up her position.
Smart girl.
Stop where you are! Stop right there!
Put your hands where I can see them.
Turn around and put
your hands in the air.
Put your hands in the air.
Do it now.
Get your hand off your weapon.
Stop where you are.
Stop. Stop where you are.
Shooter's down!
Code-4!
I need a medic! The shooter is down!
In a panic, the wife of the
alleged pentagram killer,
attempted to flee,
injuring a reporter in the process.
Of the original spree.
Our own Steve sahagan
was almost crushed
by the frantic widow. Steve?
Juarez, get on crowd
control. Get these people back.
Back, folks. Get out of the way.
Come on.
Everyone. I need
everyone to stand back!
This is a crime scene.
Opal, what happened?
I just wanted them to leave me alone.
I thought you were
gonna stay with friends.
What friends?
I tried calling.
None of them want
anything to do with me.
It's all gone... my life,
my friends, my home.
He took it all.
They can't blame you if you didn't know.
Opal, did you know?
That my husband of
42 years was a killer?
Of course not.
But there... there were
some... some things.
He'd give me jewelry that
I knew we couldn't afford.
He liked me to wear it,
and then it would disappear.
And once I-I found.
I found a pair of ladies'
underwear in the car.
I threw them away, but I didn't ask.
I didn't want to know.
Bailey.
Hey.
I can't leave you alone for a minute.
- I know.
- How's Carmichael? Is he okay?
Yeah, he's barely scratched.
He's going around telling everyone
that he was shot, though.
Well, technically, he's not wrong.
Lucy was an absolute
badass out there, though.
We're still waiting to
hear if the guy she shot's
gonna pull through.
Well, patrol found 87
guns at that guy's house.
Looks like he finally
found a reason to use 'em.
That's unbelievable.
How's the reporter?
In surgery. Opal crushed his leg.
What's gonna happen to her?
Well, about 50 reporters got
the whole thing on camera,
so there's not gonna be a lot
of wiggle room for the defense.
Yeah, the pentagram killer's last victims.
- Hey.
- Why are you here?
- The
the pentagram widow ran over a reporter.
Right, right.
I passed Tim's train test.
- Congrats.
- Yeah.
I knew you would.
Didn't you have to
get punched in the face
- or something to pass?
- I did.
I mean, she was only like 90 pounds,
but it still counts, you know.
Anyways, I came to
see if there's any news
on Lucy's shooting.
Not yet.
Do we know?
- Still waiting.
- Where is she?
All right.
They're over there, yeah.
Hey.
Are you hurt?
My god.
You didn't have to take my
hero suggestion so literally.
I don't feel like a hero at all.
Any news?
He's still in surgery right now.
What if he dies?
What if I killed that guy?
Then we'll deal with it.
Jeff budny made it through surgery.
They're taking him to the icu.
Wait, he's alive?
Now the da still needs your statement
for the shooting inquiry.
And should he die from his injuries
at a later time, the
investigation will resume.
But try not to worry about that right now.
Can the statement wait?
Yeah, tomorrow morning's fine.
Let's go.
Come on. Come on.
Let's go home.
Damn it.