- These night shifts
have got me tired.
- Well, we've got
four more hours.
Keep it together.
- Yes, sir.
Sorry, it's just,
a week of nights and I--
I still can't get
my circadian rhythm in line.
And forget about
altering my chronotype
to maximize sleep efficiency.
- Well, perhaps
it's for the best,
seeing as how
we're getting back on days
now that I finally
paid back everyone
who covered for me
while I was gone.
Hm.
- Forgetting anything?
- I don't think so.
- You sure?
- 100% sure.
- Good.
How about the suspect?
- ♪ Whoa, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you
♪ Like I know
you want me to do ♪
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Is that a present for me?
- Yep. And the beer's for me.
- Thank you.
- What?
- Nothing.
I'm--it's just, um,
gift giving isn't really
your love language, so...
- Oh, yeah.
What is my love language?
- Terse nods, mainly.
- Okay, well, I'm trying
to change things up.
- Okay.
Well, can I open it now?
- Yeah, of course.
- Oh, my God.
My killed-in-action radio?
Aww.
That is so sweet.
- Well, it gave its life
for yours,
so I thought it'd be nice
to memorialize your effort
in the Jeff Budny takedown.
- Thank you.
- Oops.
I-I forgot it was date night.
I will hide in my room.
- You don't have to do that.
- No, it's my bad.
What smells so good?
- Paella.
You want me to make you a plate
for your room?
- I would say no,
but I'd be lying.
- Yep, Bradford.
Who's this?
Understood.
I'll be there in 20.
- What's going on?
- I gotta go, sorry.
- Just wait--
- I can't.
I'll call you when I can.
- What just happened?
- I don't know.
- Can I do
a vodka soda, please?
Dr. London?
- Hi.
Uh--
- It's okay.
I know, uh, seeing a patient
in the wild is tricky.
- Sorry, I just had
a whole semester
of ethics classes
flash through my mind.
But if you're okay talking
out in the wild...
- Totally. May I?
- Mm-hmm.
So do you live around here?
- No, I actually live
on the West Side.
I just got done seeing a movie
around the corner,
and, uh, came in here
for a little nightcap.
- Drinking alone?
- Yeah, but, you know,
I kind of look at it
as a sign of self-assurance,
not so much a cry for help.
What about you?
- I...I got stood up.
- Who the hell
would stand you up?
I mean, you are a catch
and then some.
- Sorry, that's inappropriate.
- Completely.
But my ego
really appreciated it.
Okay. I should go.
- Yeah.
Or I could buy you a drink.
In a total, like,
patient-doctor kind of way.
- I really shouldn't.
- Right.
- One drink.
- All right, deal.
What you drinking?
- What's up, man?
Thanks for coming.
- I had no choice.
If Ray's alive,
we got a problem.
- He is.
I'm sure.
- How?
They found the tags, his DNA.
We saw the air strike.
There's no one who could have
walked away
from something like that.
- Yeah, that's
what I thought too.
But then a few years ago,
I started hearing stories,
that he was still alive,
working as a gun for hire
around the globe.
So I set up some trip wires
just to be sure.
That's Ray coming
through LAX yesterday.
- What the hell's
he doing here?
- His mom's dying of cancer.
- So she's who
we're staking out?
- Two houses up on the left.
No sign of Ray yet.
- So when did Ray give a crap
about anybody but himself?
- Doesn't matter.
We made a promise.
- That was a long time ago.
- Time doesn't erase
what he did.
Time doesn't bring back
our friends that he killed.
And we made a vow that
if by some miracle he survived,
we'd kill him.
And I am here
to honor that promise.
- Most of these men could be
my dad, some my grandpa.
But I'm supposed to be
some sort of authority figure.
I have cereal for dinner
at least three nights a week.
- Oh. So do I.
- Mine has
dehydrated marshmallows.
- Okay, see, that is a problem.
I should go.
- Yeah.
Uh, time to call an Uber.
- I mean, I could
give you a ride.
- Really?
- Yeah, it's not a problem.
- Okay.
- Cool.
- This is me.
Thanks for the ride.
- Yeah, no problem.
- Good night.
- 7-Adam-15, multiple callers
report shots fired,
715 Sycamore.
No associated vehicles.
I'll attach two more units.
- You got here quick.
- We were finishing up a call
around the corner,
heard the shots.
- All right, this is
as far as you go.
- We'll stage here
until you Code 4 it.
Be safe.
- Right.
Follow me.
All right, be alert.
I know you're tired.
- Well, not anymore.
Adrenaline is flowing.
- Good. Let's do this.
Juarez.
Go.
- What happened here?
- Control, 7-Adam-15,
two victims, gunshot wounds.
Still clearing house.
I'll take left. Go.
Officer Nolan!
Hey, ambulance
is right outside.
Stay with me.
- 7-Adam-15,
residence is cleared.
Code 4 for fire.
One gunshot wound victim
is unconscious but breathing.
How is she?
- Her pulse is weak.
She could bleed out.
- John?
- Back here.
She's the only one left alive.
You didn't clear the closet?
- Uh, no.
- Police. Come out now.
- Oh. Hey.
What are you doing in here?
Come here.
Come here, little one.
What are you doing?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Hey, look at this.
You don't need
to see that, okay?
- How's the mother?
- Still in surgery.
They're checking in
on the little girl.
No visible injuries.
- Yeah, her first name is Anna,
last name Hughes.
Remi's the mom, Ellis the dad,
and the older woman in the
dining room was Grandma Debra.
- You think the girl saw
what happened?
- Oh, I hope not.
She still hasn't said a word.
- I've been in contact
with CPS.
They are searching for a family
member to come to the hospital
and take custody of Anna
once she's cleared.
- You know, we still have
a whole lot of paperwork to do.
We'll probably stick around,
see how the surgery goes.
- Of course. I'll let you know
if anything changes.
- Thank you.
- Keep me updated
to the minute on this.
A family murdered
in the middle of the night
is gonna keep a lot
of people on edge.
- Yes, sir.
Now, about you not searching
the closet.
- There's no excuse, sir.
I-I saw the injured woman,
and I put her as a priority
before I finished
clearing the room.
It won't happen again.
- See that it doesn't.
If that was the shooter
in there instead of a child,
we'd both be dead.
- It's Bradford.
You know what to do.
- Hey, it's me.
Um, no idea
where you are right now,
but, uh, I'm here
if you need me.
So just call me when you can.
- Yeah, there's a back door,
but you gotta go
through the neighbor's yard
to get to it.
And there's no way
to see if Ray's inside.
- And--and if he is?
Then what?
We hog-tie him
and dump him in deep water?
- Well, I was thinking
landfill,
but if you got a boat--
- This isn't funny.
Just talking about this
is criminal conspiracy.
- I never would have thought
the Reaper would go soft on me.
- I ain't going soft.
That pact was made
a long time ago
in the anger and fog of war.
But now...
I'm a cop.
You're an army lawyer.
We've built lives.
- Yeah, well, what about
Henderson and Coyle?
They never got to build
their lives 'cause of Ray.
They deserve justice.
And we owe that to them.
- You okay?
- I wasn't much older
when my dad died.
Do you think she knows?
- I-I don't know.
Do you think
she'd even understand?
- I don't know.
- Ah.
- Her mother's out of surgery.
She flatlined on the table,
but they were able
to get her back.
She's still very much
in the woods.
- Any luck finding a relative?
- There's no immediate family
in Los Angeles,
but CPS is gonna widen
the search in the morning.
- So what happens to her now?
- And please don't say
children's shelter.
- For the short term, yes.
And if there's no relative
found, then foster care.
- Those shelters can be grim.
They're chaotic,
underfunded, understaffed.
- I agree.
Not the most ideal place
for a toddler
who just lived through
her family getting slaughtered.
- Give me a second.
I got him.
I'll get him.
Oh, he landed on his butt.
There we go.
He's all better.
Got him?
Here you go.
What do you think?
- About what?
- I'll be right back.
What about Anna staying
with us tonight?
- We aren't registered
foster parents.
It's a process.
- I'm aware,
but we're first responders.
I'm sure CPS would
sign off on it.
Anything's better than
those children's shelters.
- I don't know about that.
- It would be for one night,
or until they find a relative
or a temporary
foster situation.
But...
- But what?
- Nothing.
You're right.
- You won't regret this.
Luna.
What about Anna coming home
with us tonight?
- I don't see why not.
I'll go start
making some calls,
see if we can make it happen.
- Just like
the good old days, huh?
Staking out a potential target,
hours and hours of nothing.
- Just your bad jokes.
- Hey, those jokes were
me training to be a dad.
I got two now, Scott and Nancy.
Best kids ever.
- Yeah, must take after
their mother.
- We got movement.
- Was that Ray or his mom?
- Let's go find out.
- Hey, you think
that's a good idea?
- What do you want?
- Mrs. Watkins,
I'm Sergeant Tim Bradford.
This is Major Mark Greer.
We'd like to talk to you
about your son.
- Well, he's dead.
What else do you need to know?
- Do you mind if we come inside
for a second to talk?
- I do mind.
- We served with Ray, ma'am.
We just need a moment
of your time.
- Ugh.
Well, make it quick.
I'm not long for this life,
and I don't want to waste
what's left with you two.
- I'm so sorry to hear about
what you've been
going through, ma'am.
I lost my mom to cancer.
- Trust me, she's better off.
- Would you mind
if I use the bathroom?
- Down the hall.
- Thanks.
- Bradford,
you don't need that.
That, uh--
- What's wrong?
You look like
you've seen a ghost.
Yo, Greer.
My God, man, you got old.
- I just told them
you were dead.
Now you made me look
like an idiot.
- Calm down.
You don't look like an idiot.
Mom, why don't you, um,
give us a minute, huh?
- You're gonna cry when I die.
- We'll see.
So...
what are you two doing
at a dead guy's house, huh?
- Bring you to justice.
- Oh, yeah?
For what?
- For starters, being AWOL,
faking your own death,
felony grand theft.
You stole at least $1/2 million
from the U.S. government.
- Can you blame me?
I mean, the CIA was giving away
backpacks of cash.
No one was gonna miss it.
- You called in an air strike
on your own guys
when we came for you.
There wasn't enough
of Coyle and Henderson
to fit in a shoebox.
- That sounds really bad.
But I know that's not true.
Do you know how I know that?
Because I read
the after action report
that was signed
by the two of you.
- The only reason
the report reads that way
is so that your wife
and daughter
could get your death benefits.
- I never asked for that.
You knew she was about a month
away from "Dear John"-ing me.
But thanks
to your bleeding hearts,
I'm now untouchable.
I mean, you bring me
in right now,
you've got to tell Uncle Sam
about your big lie, right?
And you'll, what,
be retroactively
dishonorably discharged
and most likely
get fired
from your current jobs.
So you can arrest me,
it's okay.
Come on.
Here I am.
No?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
I'm gonna be here
to watch the old lady croak,
and then get back
to what I was doing.
And we are never going
to see each other again.
How does that sound?
Sweet.
Been really great catching up
with my old war buddies.
Greer.
You really do look old as hell.
- That go how you thought
it would, Reaper?
All we accomplished
was letting that guy know
we're coming for him.
Gonna be twice as hard
to take him out now.
- It has been a long time
since I've tucked in a toddler.
- How'd it feel?
- Wonderful.
I do think I tweaked my back
just a little bit.
- Oh, no.
- All right, we are gonna need
to make a list.
- Yes, we are.
We need diapers, baby wipes.
- Food--Cheerios.
Henry loved Cheerios.
Milk--we're out of milk.
- And we need
some baby toys, probably?
- Yeah, definitely toys.
- And we need to do
some babyproofing,
'cause this is dangerous.
- Yeah, okay.
Anything big
should be pulled down.
- Uh, these corners
are really sharp.
- Pointy things, for sure.
I'm regretting
those succulents now.
- How bad do you think this
is gonna screw the kid up?
- Depends on what you saw
and where she goes from here.
- Lila was older than Anna
when she saw me get attacked,
but I always wonder how much
of that stayed with her.
- She's one of the most
well-adjusted kids
I've ever met.
You got no worries there.
- Any clarity on the parents?
- Mom had a suspended sentence
for possession.
Went through a diversion
program successfully
and seems to have been clean.
Father was in and out of jail.
Couple drug cases,
one assault charge.
- Is this their past
coming back?
- Maybe.
Although they seemed
to turn things around
since Anna arrived.
Both parents were employed,
kept their noses clean.
- All right, we should dig
into their financials.
Things might have gotten tight
with the kid in the picture.
Maybe the dad had
to reach back out
to some of his friends
in the drug business.
- Oh, uh, what's that?
- Oh, it's Blair's jacket.
She left it in my car
last night.
Oh, do you mind if we, um, stop
by her office to drop it off?
- Who's Blair?
- My therapist.
- You went out
with your therapist last night?
- No, we ran into each other.
It was just a drink.
Totally innocent.
Although I was picking up
some vibes.
- That crosses so many lines.
You--you know that you're
not supposed to go out
with your therapist, right?
- Well, me and Lil' Gurkin
used to hang out
with Dr. Shrink all the time.
- Lil'--D--
so wait, wait, wait, what?
- Dr. Shrink.
That was my last therapist.
That's just what we called him.
- Okay.
And was this therapist
licensed?
- No.
- What?
- Hey, you think Blair left her
jacket in my car on purpose?
Like, to have an excuse
to see me again?
- She does have an excuse
to see you again.
Therapy.
Yeah.
- She is adorable.
- She really is.
- You know, when your child
grows up and leaves,
you don't just miss them.
You miss all
the versions of them
like they're all these separate
individual people.
You miss the--
the infant version,
the toddler version,
the skinny 10-year-old version.
And then the man
that Henry's become.
- That's why people keep
having kids,
to get back to those versions
they miss.
Oh.
They should develop
a time machine.
It'd certainly make
things simpler.
- Mm. And cheaper.
- And cheaper.
Ah, it's Luna.
- Mm.
- Hey. Nice to see ya.
- Hey.
- What's--what's wrong?
- Anna's mom, Remi,
she died a little while ago.
- So what happens now?
- We don't have great options.
She'll end up at a shelter
for a week or two
until we can find
a foster family
that will take her in.
Unless--
- Unless what?
- Unless you would be willing
to keep her
until we can place her
with a family.
- What do you think about that?
- I think that's a bad idea.
- Would you give us
a minute, please?
- Of course.
- What's going on?
- Nothing.
- No, not nothing.
Any other day,
you are generous to a fault.
- Well, it's--
it's not about that.
I-I want what's best for Anna.
And I think bonding with us
for a few weeks is only gonna
damage her further
on the back end
when, you know,
they pull her away from us.
- Okay. Maybe.
But that's not really
why you're hesitating, is it?
- When I was 15,
I was babysitting
for my four-year-old
neighbor, Ryan.
I got distracted for a second.
And when I turned around,
he was in the pool.
I jumped in.
I pulled him out.
He was fine.
But ever since then...
I was almost the reason
my neighbors lost their son.
I'm not mom material.
- Okay.
Um, I disagree.
But I understand.
Let's just say goodbye to Anna.
- Wait.
Okay.
- Are you sure?
I don't want to do this
if you're not comfortable.
- How can I make this about me
after everything
she's been through?
Luna, we will take Anna
until you find a family member
or a good foster home.
- That's amazing.
You're amazing for doing this.
- Oh, sorry, this is Wesley.
I'm just gonna grab this.
- Yeah.
- Hey, what's up?
- Uh, "what's up?"
it's your deposition today,
Oscar's lawsuit.
- Wesley, I completely forgot.
I am so sorry.
- Okay, I need you to start
putting these things
in your calendar.
- I am.
I did. I have.
It's--it is.
I just--
I-I have so much going on.
- Look, it's clearly
a frivolous case,
but until I can
get it dismissed,
you need
to take this seriously.
- No, you're absolutely right.
I-I am on my way.
Crap.
Oscar's deposition, I forgot.
It should only take
a couple of hours.
I'm so sorry to leave you.
- It's fine. It's fine.
- Are you sure?
I could try
to take her with me.
- Yeah, don't be silly.
We'll be fine.
And I really want
this Oscar situation behind us.
- You and me both.
- Thorsen, Chen,
what's happenin'?
- Smitty, I'm pretty sure
you're not supposed
to be getting in therapy
while you're on shift.
- Oh, I'm not a patient here.
It's where I come
to take my breaks.
Plus, they got
top-notch snackage
and the mood is super zen.
- Yeah, pretty sure
that's not okay either.
- Tomato, to-mah-to.
Snackage.
- That's a new one.
- Yeah, I know.
- Officer Thorsen?
I don't have an appointment
with you today, do I?
- No, I just, uh,
brought you your jacket.
- Oh, you didn't have
to do that.
You could have just brought it
to our next session.
- Thought you might need it.
Never know, it might be
your favorite jacket.
Thanks.
That was nice of you.
- Okay.
Well, back to work.
Okay, I'm confused.
- Are you sure she was
flirting with you last night?
- I thought she was.
- Were you drinking?
- I only had one.
- Oh.
- Oh, no.
Am I that guy?
- What?
- The one that thinks
every girl is hitting on him?
- You know who we could ask?
- Who?
- Celina.
- Funny.
- I know.
- Yeah, funny.
- I'm hilarious.
Bye, Smitty.
- We're not killing him.
- You are looking at this
all wrong.
Ray is already dead.
We're just making sure
he stays that way.
- You can hide behind
that idea all you want,
but we both know
it'll give you no comfort
when the nightmares come.
- So what?
We let him get away with it?
- No.
We come clean--
about everything.
- Not a chance.
Ray is right.
We say anything,
it'll blow up our lives.
I will lose my career,
my family.
- I wouldn't let that happen.
I'll take the fall.
I was squad leader.
It'll all be on me.
- I signed those
after action reports too.
- I'll say I made you sign 'em.
- No one will buy it!
All right, you are gonna
lose everything,
destroy my life, and then
Ray will still be out there.
There is only one way
out of this.
- I can't.
And I won't let you.
- You would arrest me
for killing that scumbag?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Then I'm out.
And whatever death and
destruction Ray causes next,
that's on you.
- Well, it's undisputed
that Officer Nolan wanted
to inflict pain
on Oscar Hutchinson.
- Untrue.
It is very much in dispute.
- Are we keeping you up,
Officer Nolan?
Is my client's life
not important to you?
- Sorry, no.
I've been pulling doubles
lately, and last night,
we took home a little girl
whose family had been murdered.
- Please strike that
from the record.
Officer Nolan is clearly
trying to paint himself
in a positive light
for the court.
- Not at all,
though I can understand
how any act of generosity
you would see as manipulative.
- Let's get back on track.
- Yes. Let's.
Officer Nolan, would you read
the highlighted text exchange
from the day of the attack
on Oscar Hutchinson?
"Why can't this guy just
get shanked in prison?"
- And who did you send
that text to?
- My girlfriend at the time,
Bailey Nune.
- And who were
you referring to?
Who do you wish to see, quote,
"Shanked in prison"?
- I don't wish to see anyone--
- Just answer the question.
Who were you referring to
in the text?
- Oscar Hutchinson.
But this was taken
out of context.
- Under what context do
you wish to see my client dead?
And to what lengths
were you willing to go
to make sure that happened?
- This is just a man
venting his frustration
about work to his wife.
Nothing more.
- Mm.
Let's move on
to the second text,
shall we, Officer Nolan,
if you please?
- Oh, wow.
- Oh, yes.
This is a cool fort,
don't you think?
- Yes.
- And we can feel
really safe in here, huh?
I love seeing you smile.
You can line 'em all up.
Yes.
Oh, I would love to sit closer.
It's pretty cool in here, huh?
- Yeah.
- Oh, good, you're not dead.
- I'm sorry.
- Not good enough.
I've spent the last 36 hours
imagining you bleeding out
at a variety
of Los Angeles landmarks.
- I would have called you
if I could.
- Telling me you're alive
is not optional.
What the hell are you into
that's making you so crazy?
- I can't tell you.
- Why?
- Because even knowing about it
would put you at risk
with the department.
- You committed a crime?
- No.
I mean, no, not--
not technically.
- But you've done something
that I would be compelled
to report, and if I didn't,
I would get disciplined?
- I'm not gonna have
my drama infect you.
- Then what are you doing here?
- I-I came to see you.
- And what?
Order take-in?
Watch TV?
Pretend like
nothing's going on?
- No. I--
- If you are not here
to tell me the truth...
I need you to leave.
- Understood.
- Hey, how are we doing
on the multiple homicides?
- Yeah, we're coming up
empty so far.
- No eyewitnesses,
not a lot of doorbell cameras
in that neighborhood.
- Yeah, and we talked
to some coworkers,
and they did confirm
that they had turned
their lives around.
- Now a dead end on ballistics.
No match.
No hits on any of the prints.
- We should expand
the canvassing area.
I'll add some units,
widen the grid.
- Wait, uh,
it looks like the Hughes
got a payment
every third of the month
for $300
like clockwork.
- Drug payments?
Maybe the dad got back
in the game.
- You know a lot of junkies
on a payment plan?
- So...what?
- Rent check?
I mean, they have had
money problems.
And that back room
felt different
than the rest of the house.
There were no personal items,
and it had a dead bolt on it.
Maybe they took on a tenant.
- A tenant that disappears
after an entire family
is slaughtered.
- Looks like we have a suspect.
- Hey, I need your help
figuring out what's
going on with Tim.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Hi, how are you?
I'm fine. Thanks.
Um, that's a lie.
Okay, so two nights ago,
Tim got this crazy phone call
and then he disappeared.
Then he called in sick.
And now he says that
if he tells me what's going on,
I could get fired.
- Well, then I--
I guess it's a good thing
he didn't tell you.
- Would you accept
that reasoning from Bailey?
- No.
- Look, if I knew what was
going on, maybe I could help--
we could help.
- Right.
But if he won't tell you,
I don't see what choice
you have.
What's going on?
- We ID'd the guy renting
the back bedroom
from the Hughes.
- Midnight shift
brought him in.
- Uh, I have to--
- N-no, of course.
Good luck.
- Okay, you too.
And I'm here if you need me.
- All right, we got warm milk,
sound machine.
We are ready for nap.
Anna?
Sweetie?
Come on out, sweetie.
We're not playing
hide-and-seek.
Anna?
Anna. Honey.
Oh, my God.
Where's John?
- Hi, it's John Nolan.
Leave a message at the beep.
- Anna, sweetie.
Oh, sweetie.
You had me so scared.
Oh, come here.
Oh, sweetie, I was so scared.
Okay.
Oh, it's kind of nice in here.
I actually get why you like it.
- Where were you
night before last?
- Uh, I was at home
with my wife.
You can call her.
She'll tell you.
- What's your relationship
to the Hughes?
- Ellis and I go way back.
Uh, I work in Brentwood,
live in Victorville.
It's about a two-hour drive
on a good day.
I rent a room from them
on the nights that I work late.
But I swear,
I would never hurt them.
- You know what happened?
- It's all over the news.
Is Anna okay?
- She's safe.
- Look, I--I know
I should have came forward
and said something, but, look,
I saw what he did to them,
and I was scared.
- He?
- Yeah, Bad Rod.
Ellis won a lottery ticket
a couple days ago,
was bragging how he hit big,
and Rod seemed real interested.
- I couldn't find her.
And suddenly, I was 15 again,
and that little boy
was face down in the pool.
I can't believe I ever thought
I could do this.
- I understand how that trauma
could imprint on you.
But that little boy was okay,
and so is Anna.
- I am terrified
I'm gonna fail her.
- We all are.
One time, I accidentally
slammed Dominique's finger
in the sliding glass door.
I can still hear her scream.
- Mm.
- You don't have to be perfect
to take care
of this little girl.
You just have to care enough
to get through
the scary moments.
But I can take her with me,
if you want.
No judgment whatsoever.
- No. Let her sleep.
- You got this.
- A lottery ticket?
That's why he killed
that little girl's family?
- Not even a lottery ticket,
a scratch-off for $1,500.
- If he's willing to kill
three people for $1,500,
what's he gonna do
to stay out of prison?
- All right, Nolan, Juarez,
you two cover the back.
You three take the front.
If he doesn't go quietly,
we hold the perimeter
and let SWAT do their thing.
All right, go.
- Mom's probably been searched
a dozen times,
tired of having a gun
stuck in her face.
You wanna low-key this?
- All right,
we're gonna low-key this.
Roderick may not be home,
and we don't want to traumatize
this woman any more
than we have to.
- Roger that.
We're in position.
No movement in the house.
- LAPD. Mrs. Eaves?
- We have a search warrant
for this house
and an arrest warrant
for Roderick Eaves.
- He's not here.
That's what that sign says.
I haven't seen or heard
from him in months.
So don't go tearing up
my house.
- A search warrant
isn't a choice, ma'am.
Please step outside.
- Uh, floor gets creaky
after I vacuum.
- Yeah, that's not a thing.
Come here.
We have movement inside.
Perimeter hold.
We are making entry.
What the hell is he shooting?
- High-velocity slug rounds.
Control, we have
a barricaded suspect
with some type of long gun.
Send SWAT to our location.
- I got an open window.
You want tear gas?
- Do it.
- Cover me.
- Clear.
Control, Code 4.
We have suspect in custody.
Mobilize an RA unit for a GSW.
- All right.
Everyone okay?
- All in one piece.
- Hey, hey.
You okay?
Heard it got a little dicey
out there today.
- Oh, yeah.
A bit of a soup sandwich,
but we all came out all right.
- All over
a scratch-off ticket?
Yeah.
Oh, hey, I got
some good news for you.
- Oscar died?
- You have to stop
joking like that.
- Even though he stabbed you?
- Yeah, fair enough.
A judge granted
the motion to dismiss.
- So it's over?
- For you.
The judge said you had
the lowest tier of culpability.
The sheriff stationed
outside the hospital room
was primarily responsible
for Oscar's safety.
- Wesley, that is great.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- I'd say get some sleep,
but I know you got a toddler
at your house, so--
- Oh, yeah, no.
Sleep is out the window.
- Ooh, yeah.
- I need to clear the air
on something.
Um, look, the other night--
- Totally my fault.
I should never have said yes
to that drink.
It was a violation of
our professional relationships,
and I could get
into a lot of trouble.
- T-trust me, you won't.
I would never narc you out.
- I know that,
but I never should have
put you in a position
to make that choice.
I understand if you want
to switch therapists.
- No.
No, not at all.
Look, you are the first person
that I've ever felt
comfortable opening up to,
and I can't lose that.
You know, so no matter the--
the physical attraction
we felt--
- Aaron.
I need to make this very clear.
There was and is no attraction
on my end.
I need you to understand that.
- Understood. Yeah.
Uh, glad we cleared the air
on that.
See you next session.
- Have a good week.
- Thank you.
You too.
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
I am not calling,
not searching, not stalking.
I'm just being a good
girlfriend and trusting my man.
- Worst country song ever.
Still no word?
- I mean, we talked last night.
- That's good.
- More like I got heated
and he just stood there,
so I don't know.
I'm at a loss.
- I've got an idea.
Let's put a tracker
on his truck.
- You--you are
a bad influence.
- No. You're just
a really good teacher.
- Wh-what?
- You think I haven't learned
a thing or two
living with a cop
who aced undercover school?
- Okay.
What have you learned?
- Never hold your coffee
with your gun hand.
- Yes, that is actually
very useful.
However, you do not have a gun.
So what else?
- Keep your head on a swivel.
- What is this?
Oh, balance.
Good.
- ♪ In my prayer,
I don't speak ♪
♪ But with my hands
and on my knees ♪
♪ When I ask, I receive
♪ Don't play fair,
don't be sweet ♪
♪ It's in the air
that I breathe ♪
♪ Understand it's
up my sleeve ♪
♪ Well, in my head,
it's in my sleep ♪
♪ With my hands, in my teeth
- Oh, my gosh.
I love what you've done here.
I see a pig,
but I also see a cat.
More of a pig-cat.
Kind of brilliant.
She's brilliant.
- Okay.
- Pardon me.
- Let's do it.
- Do what?
- Foster her.
I know we decided not
to have kids,
but this feels like fate.
- Yeah. No, it does.
Are y--are you sure
you're all right with this?
- Yeah.
I-I-I mean, I'm terrified,
but I can run
into burning buildings.
I can do this.
- Of course you can.
This is gonna be great.
- Yes.
- This is gonna be so great.
both: Hi.
- Come in.
Hi.
- Great news.
John, Bailey,
this is Don Hughes,
Anna's uncle from Tampa.
- Oh, great to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- He's gonna take Anna
to live with him.
- That's--that's fantastic.
- Yeah.
- Thank you so much
for taking care of her.
- Oh, no, of course. Yeah.
- She's amazing.
- Yeah, she's been great.
- Hey, sweetheart.
How you doing?
- Aw.
- Aw. Fantastic.
This is goodbye,
so high fives, little one.
- Bye, sweetie.
Yeah.
- Let me get her settled
in the rental.
I'm gonna head right
to the airport.
- Okay.
- Come on.
Ready?
- You both did an amazing job.
I can't thank you enough.
- You okay?
- No.
- Yeah, me too.
- Damn it.