Celina, look out!
Officer down.
Help him.
Tell me what you're feeling.
Frustration.
But not fear?
No.
Today was the first time
during this exercise
that your heart rate
didn't spike.
You remained calm.
Why do you think that is?
Because I know
there's no way I could have
stopped what happened.
That's right.
The men who ambushed you
and Officer Juarez
rigged the game.
No matter which way you turned,
whether you split up
or stayed together,
even if you called it in,
none of that
would have made a difference
because they were ready.
One of you was gonna be shot
that night.
And who knows?
If you hadn't made
the decisions you did,
maybe it would have been
Celina, instead of you.
No, you're... you're right.
Um, I've been blaming myself.
Like, if I had been smarter,
I could have somehow avoided it.
But it was out of my control.
Congratulations,
Officer Thorsen.
In my professional opinion,
you are ready
to return to active duty.
Oh, I'm just really excited
to get back to work.
- Yeah.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you
♪ Like I know
you want me to do ♪
Look, I told you I'm fine.
I'll just retake the
detective's exam in two years.
It's not a big deal.
You know,
every time a woman in my life
has said she was fine,
she most definitely was not.
I'm not gonna pretend like
I wasn't a little disappointed.
But I've made my peace with it.
Plus, I'm a professional.
Unless you want me to be upset.
No, of course not.
Hey, Lucy, I heard about
the detective exam.
- Tough break.
- Yes, thank you.
I'm fine.
Whenever Bailey says
she's fine like that,
I up my life insurance.
There he is.
Everyone drive safe out there.
Thorsen is back in the shop.
As always, Detective,
your unwavering support
means the world to me.
- Mm.
- Ah, don't fret.
In Harper speak, that's
practically an "I love you."
Bradford, got a minute?
Congrats on being cleared.
- Thanks.
- So any nerves?
Not really.
Um, I feel strong in mind,
body, and spirit.
- I'm ready.
- Thorsen's not ready.
What's the first thing
an officer returning
from injury worries about?
Gettin' hurt again.
Especially after
a near-fatal like Thorsen's.
You afraid he's gonna go
turtle up when things get real?
I don't wanna wait to find out.
In this business, we don't
have the luxury of do-overs.
So you want me
to take him out today
to get punched in the face.
Officially, I want you
to supervise his ability
to cope with stress,
both mental and physical.
You got it.
Let's see how he does
against the TRAIN.
Thorsen, you're with me.
Metro needs a support officer.
Oh, um, yes, sir.
Ooh.
You know what it means
to "turtle up," Thorsen?
I don't think so, sir.
It happens when
an officer returns
to the job after a trauma,
put under some kind of pressure,
usually physical,
for the first time.
Instead of falling back
on their training,
they shrink into a shell,
where they feel safe.
So you think
I'm gonna turtle up?
Maybe.
If you do, there are lots
of companies looking
for delivery guys
with a good driving record.
Well, actually,
my fallback career is gonna be
influencer/shoe designer.
But I-I see what you're saying.
Oh, so that's why
I'm riding with you.
So I gotta pass, what, some
type of Tim test so I don't...
It's called the TRAIN.
Stands for Tactical,
Responsive, Assertive,
Investigative, and Nerve.
And I'm gonna test you
on all five major functions
in stress environments.
Evaluate, improvise,
adapt, and overcome.
You ready for this?
Bring it on.
So how did you like riding
with Sergeant Bradford?
It was very educational.
Both he and Detective Harper
have very distinctive styles.
Dispatch, you said the RP was
on the south side of the park?
Affirmative, 7-Adam-15.
Okay, so did they, uh, like,
say anything about me?
They did.
Like all rookies,
you are a work in progress.
Over here!
Hi, I'm Officer Nolan.
This is Officer Juarez.
You called about a body?
Yeah, it's, uh, in there.
Um, someone jammed the lock,
but when I finally got it open,
she...
she was just lying there...
It's okay. It's okay.
Stay here.
We're gonna need to get some
information from you, okay?
Okay?
- After you.
- Yep.
Oh.
Overdose?
No.
Lividity in the cheeks.
She died facedown
and was moved here.
Looks like a homicide.
Let's call it in.
Control, requesting detectives
for a possible homicide.
Welcome to your first test.
Let me guess...
that's the stress environment?
Ah, it's a little more
than that.
Man inside is
Tyson Kalashnikov, 6'4", 275.
Has a warrant
for a missed court appearance.
Last time he was arrested,
he broke the cop's nose.
I assume calling
for backup is cheating?
Train's leaving,
Officer Thorsen.
Okay, let's do this.
Police! Open up!
It's open.
Clear!
Tyson, show yourself!
Could one of you get me a beer?
I moved the picnic blanket
so we could examine her head.
She was definitely
moved postmortem.
Obvious blunt force trauma
to the head.
What's this under her shirt?
Huh, what is that?
It's the signature
of the Pentagram Killer.
Pardon us just one moment.
So the Pentagram Killer
is wanted
in connection to a string
of unsolved homicides
in the early 2000s.
His victims were all
middle-aged females.
He'd carve a pentagram
into their midsections
after he killed them.
Then in 2009, he just stopped.
Hulu just dropped
a docuseries on him.
Maybe the renewed notoriety
inspired him
to come out of retirement.
The hysteria was real.
I was away at college,
and I made my brothers
escort my mom everywhere.
Mm, scary that they never
caught the guy.
Well, the city threw
everything they had at it,
multiple agencies working 24/7.
My first sergeant was
on the task force.
Oh, speaking of,
whenever we respond
to a potentially
high-profile event,
it's important
to notify the watch commander.
Yes, sir.
Adam-200, be advised, our DB
might be a possible victim
of the Pentagram Killer.
Officer Juarez!
Did I do something wrong?
As her TO, that is on you.
Yes, ma'am.
I am sorry, ma'am.
Officer Suarez,
I should have been clearer.
You never give out that kind
of sensitive information
over the radio.
Now every news organization
or hobbyist
with a scanner has it.
Oh, my God.
I didn't think that...
Uh, did I hear someone say
"Pentagram Killer" on the radio?
- Um...
- I'm... I'm so sorry.
Is that really bad?
Cases like this capture
the public's attention.
People call in with tips,
trying to be a part of it.
But most of them are
a complete waste of time.
Yeah, because when people panic,
they call 911
at every bump in the night.
So no, that...
that was not ideal.
Okay, is there anything
I can do to help?
Just take the witness back
to the station,
and maybe stay off the radio.
Yes, ma'am.
We're on it.
- I'm sorry.
- Mm.
Come on.
You want me to start canvassing?
Uh, no, we need
to secure the perimeter first.
Um, there's no one watching
the northwest corner.
Probably because it's where
the hell dumpsters are.
Yeah, of course.
Whatever you need.
As a patrol officer, I'm here
to support your investigation
- in any way that I can.
- Great.
We're gonna head back
to the station
and dig into this case file
and let crime scene
do their thing.
Come here.
Got it?
Yo, just lean him up
against the car.
Control, Bradford, can I get a
transport van to our location?
What's that?
No idea.
I'll check it out.
Tyson?
Tyson? It's me.
Hi.
You looking for Tyson?
- Have you heard the good news?
- What good news?
Our lord and savior has come
to save our souls.
Well, amen, sister.
- Ha.
- Can I see some ID?
Ma'am?
Excuse me. Ma'am.
No!
Hey, Harper, uh,
I just found a pile of vomit
on the far northwest corner
of the park.
Oh, lucky you.
It's unlikely to be related,
but we still need
to collect it, just in case.
I will have TID process it
as soon as they're done
with the scene.
Oh, um, how long
do you think that'll take?
Uh, a couple hours, four tops.
In the meantime,
keep an eye on it.
It's my lucky...
It's my lucky day.
- I wouldn't want to be her.
- Ooh.
Man, that man is
an Olympic-level yeller.
You got an ID on our vic?
Yeah, Cheryl Budny, 42,
works at Lincoln Junior High.
She left at her usual time
around 5:00 p.m...
didn't show up today.
She live close by the park?
No, Culver City.
So that means that the dump site
is most likely related
to the killer.
Yeah, Cheryl's brother lives
over in Little Armenia.
He should be here any minute.
I reserved interview three
for us.
Great.
You still have
all your fingers and toes?
Sergeant Grey was very fair.
And again, I'm...
I'm very sorry.
Don't worry about us.
It's you guys
who are gonna pay the price.
What do you mean?
Any more evidence pointing
to the Pentagram Killer?
Some of the signature
qualities match
his previous victims,
but all are public knowledge.
Which means we can't
decisively say it's him.
Nolan, I need you guys 10-8.
Calls are backing up.
26 pending related
to the Pentagram.
And that's the price.
Cheryl's next of kin
is on his way.
Call us if you get
anything interesting.
Phone call. On the phone.
All right, what have we got,
Officer Thorsen?
Well, she attempted to contact
a well-known criminal
and one suspect.
She ran when she saw
my uniform, giving me
probable cause to believe
that she also was engaged
in criminal activity.
And she also held $15,000
in cash.
And cash is frequently used
to finance and conceal
criminal activity.
Not bad.
Is that enough to arrest?
I mean, she tried
to scratch my face off.
So there's a 1-48 right there.
But I'm actually more interested
in why she had all that money
on her.
Good. Under stress,
you made a tactical entry.
You were responsive
to criminal activity
and assertive when
she tried to run.
You may build
this TRAIN just yet.
Well, what about "nerve"?
I mean, she hit me with her bag,
and did you see her nails?
Nope.
Hurry up and process 'em.
We got work to do.
Jeff Budny?
I'm Detective Lopez.
This is Detective Harper.
If you follow us,
we have a room set up.
I got 30 minutes left
on my lunch break.
Can't you just say whatever it
is you need to say right here?
Uh, well, we're sorry
to have to tell you this,
but it's about
your sister, Cheryl.
What about her?
She's deceased.
What?
What happened?
It was a homicide.
- I'm so sorry.
- A homicide?
Wait, wait, wait.
That's... when? How?
Listen,
I know this is difficult,
but we really would like
to speak with you somewhere
where there's more privacy.
Just tell me what happened
to my sister.
They discovered her body
in a park this morning.
And that's really all
we can say right now.
That's all you can say?
Did you two get along?
I mean, when was the last time
you saw or spoke with her?
We were tight, all right?
I don't know.
I talked to her
a couple days ago.
Wednesday, maybe.
I don't know.
Can you think of anyone
who wanted to harm her?
No.
She worked at a grade school.
Well, I'm sorry,
but I have to ask,
what were you doing last night?
You mean while
my sister was being murdered?
Yeah, watching
the Laker game at Barney's.
20 people can vouch for me.
Listen, I know you're upset,
and I cannot even imagine
what you are going through
right now.
But the more you give us,
the faster
we can find who did this.
I can't do this right now, okay?
There's people I need to call.
My mom, jeez.
I gotta call my mom.
We understand,
but as soon as possible,
we need to sit down with you
and get a full statement.
Call us when you're ready.
Any time, day or night.
Well, he seems genuinely upset.
Yeah, still gonna check
that alibi, though.
Damn straight.
All right, Sarge,
both suspects are booked.
Do you want a medal?
No, sir.
I just really would like
to figure out
what a suburban housewife
was doing with all that cash.
And why bring it to Tyson?
Opioids, gambling,
debt, pirated movies.
Who knows?
Who cares?
They never completed
the transaction.
If there's more to it,
shouldn't we dig
a little deeper?
Good.
The I in TRAIN stands
for Investigative Initiative.
That's two I's.
Never mind.
You don't get the I
unless it's under stress.
So we're gonna make
this interesting.
You've got nine minutes
to get to the bottom of this.
If you can't,
I'm gonna recommend we extend
your probation and return you
to the FTO program.
Nine minutes? Why not ten?
Now it's eight minutes,
47 seconds.
Ticktock.
So why were you attempting
to pay Tyson Kalashnikov
$15,000 in cash?
'Cause he's my gigolo.
I got a thing for guys
who can't move their arms.
Mm-hmm.
Hello?
Yes, arm casts.
Very sexy.
Oh, your husband's in prison.
I mean, your husband
is Austin Walker,
doing three to five
in San Quentin
for embezzlement.
- Is that right?
- Austin made a mistake.
Yeah, one with very serious
consequences.
Now, did you know
that Tyson did four stints
in San Quentin?
And that's where
he's heading back to now.
And it looks like
he's also the lieutenant
of the Devil's Crown
prison gang.
They run your husband's prison.
Okay, so connecting those dots,
I'm guessing that you paid Tyson
to keep your husband safe
while he's inside.
Is that what's happening?
Tyson said that if I didn't pay
him the money by tomorrow,
Austin was as good as dead.
He's all I have.
I didn't have a choice.
I didn't... I didn't know
what else to do.
Okay, look, don't worry.
All right?
I'm gonna help you.
Sir, I need to call the prison
and have Austin Walker put
into protective custody,
like, right now.
Already done,
and you still have 25 seconds.
Are you sure
your investigation is complete?
Yeah, I think so.
I mean, it's just
a classic protection racket.
Are you asking me,
or are you telling me?
No, I'm telling...
I'm telling you.
Okay.
Unless I'm missing something.
I didn't say that.
Time's up.
Ooh, listen to this one.
A man says
that his neighbor's cat
is possessed by the Pentagram.
There's gotta be one tip
on that call line
that is not totally insane.
Uh, let's see.
A lady with
a devil-worshipping nephew.
- Skip it.
- Teenage girl thought
that her mailman was
the Pentagram
and was there to snatch her.
Oh, she actually sprayed him
with a hose.
- Next.
- Old lady claims her husband
committed the murders
while he was on shore leave.
Was he in the Navy?
It looks like
commercial fisherman.
- Attach us to that.
- Really?
Commercial fisherman work
a lot at night...
perfect excuse to be out late, hunting.
All of our victims had ligature
marks from being tied up.
You know who's really good
at tying knots?
- Fishermen?
- Bingo.
Mrs. Opal Jesper?
We're here about
a tip you called in.
I'm... I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done that.
It was a mistake.
Ma'am...
you said your husband
is the Pentagram Killer.
That does not sound
like a mistake.
I didn't know what to do.
I found this.
Sandra Owens.
That's the first victim.
Ma'am, where is
your husband right now?
He's been dead for seven years.
Probably more inside.
Thanks very much.
Thanks.
What's gonna happen to me?
Well, the detectives
are gonna have
a few more questions for you
back at the station.
At the station?
- Will you be there?
- No, ma'am.
I'm a patrol officer,
not an investigator.
Oh.
Um, I'll tell you what.
Why don't you take my card?
If you need anything,
give me a call.
My mobile number's on there,
all right?
If you'll excuse us
just for a moment?
Thanks.
Hey.
That widow looks like
she's sweet on you.
Yeah, Nolan gave her his number.
Yes, I was trying
to build rapport.
- Did it work?
- Hard to say.
She insists she didn't know
anything about the murders
until after her husband died
and she found the trophies.
I mean, how could
she not have known?
Well, her husband wasn't
on the original suspect list,
which means that he was good
at flying under the radar.
Well, at least we can
eliminate the Pentagram Killer
as a suspect
in Cheryl Budny's case.
Let's hope his copycat
isn't as skilled
at covering his tracks.
Nolan, Juarez.
So I understand
you took the call.
Yes, sir.
We got lucky.
Well, actually,
Officer Nolan picked it out.
- He thought it sounded credible.
- Nice catch.
Look, the mayor asked me
to give a press conference
announcing the identity
of the Pentagram Killer.
I'd like you two to be there
so I can recognize your work.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, sir.
All right, go get cleaned up.
You're gonna be on TV.
Do you think I have time
for a blowout?
Absolutely not.
- No?
- Come on.
You ready?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Is that the widow?
It must be.
You know, I almost attached
to that call.
But I got pulled to a 2-11 that
turned out to be a false alarm.
Then you'd be the one on TV,
and Primm would have realized
what a giant mistake he made
torpedoing
your detective's exam.
Yeah, something like that.
Instead, I spent the day
breathing in hot dumpster fumes
while standing guard
over a pile of puke
for three hours
on the off chance
it belonged to our killer.
- Did it?
- Nope.
It was a sick dog.
Okay, so you had a crappy day.
You've had 'em before,
and you'll have 'em again.
The best part about
being on patrol is
you never know
what's gonna happen.
Maybe tomorrow,
you'll be the big hero.
I would just settle
for not having to deal
with any bodily fluids.
Yeah, don't be too greedy.
So do you really believe
the widow had no idea?
I don't know.
I mean, there was a time
when I couldn't have conceived
of not being able to tell
that my partner was keeping
something from me, but...
Then I went and hid
a whole husband from you.
Yeah, pretty much.
But you know what?
Getting through that
made us stronger.
- Yeah.
- What about you?
Do you think if you found out
I was a murderer
would you turn me in?
Absolutely.
Not a moment's hesitation.
I think you should be more
worried if I did hesitate.
- Yeah.
- What about you?
Well, as a cop,
it'd be my duty to arrest you.
But I have to say,
I would be pretty handy
at helping you hide a body.
So romantic.
I know, right?
Hey.
How'd today go?
Uh, good, I think.
Sergeant Bradford said
something to me today
that made me think I need
to dig deeper on our case,
but you ever read something
ten times
and still feel like
you're missing the point of it?
Performing under pressure
takes many forms.
Sometimes physical,
so you feel nervous.
Other times, mental.
And you just can't see
the forest from the trees.
Yeah, well,
all I can see is trees.
So any advice?
Yeah, stop thinking about it.
Take a walk.
Take a shower.
Turn your brain off.
Let your mind find the answer.
In other words, go home.
Yes, sir.
Sleep couldn't hurt.
That's right.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Hey, uh, did you come over
here just to check on me,
or did you need something?
It can keep till the morning.
I mean, I'm here now.
What's up?
I just received a call
from San Quentin Prison.
And apparently they failed
to grasp the urgency
of your request
to put Austin Walker
into protective custody.
When they finally went
to move him,
he was already dead.
Sorry, son.
That sounds like
quite the first day back.
It was.
I mean, in some ways,
I feel really good about it.
You know, I didn't freeze,
and I handled every crazy
obstacle Tim threw at me.
But for the day
to end like that...
When your watch commander
told you
that man had been killed,
- how did you feel?
- Frustrated.
You realize that's
the exact word you used
yesterday after
our visualization exercise?
Well, it's frustrating,
you know,
knowing I can be doing
everything right
and things still go wrong.
Lack of control is scary,
especially when your job
involves so much violence.
Hey, when you start
to notice those feelings,
try focusing on the things
you can control.
Tyson is still in custody,
and I can work
on connecting him to the murder,
but what I still don't get is,
if Stacy had until today
to pay the protection money,
why was her husband murdered
last night?
I did miss something.
So our victim had
lots of enemies.
At first, Cheryl's neighbors
and coworkers were
a little hesitant to speak ill
of the dead, but...
Yeah, but once they got
going, they would not stop.
They would not stop.
That tracks with
what we found online.
Her school's unofficial message
board has an entire subgroup
devoted to hating on her.
The most extreme comments
coming from a user
going by the handle
GridironGangsta.
We traced the account back
to this guy, Conrad Bataglia.
No criminal history, but he
lives with his wife, Justine,
a mile away from the park,
and he coaches football
at Cheryl's school.
So he's a gridiron something.
Let me give you
a few highlights.
Um, "She deserves cancer."
"I fantasize about shoving
a stapler down her throat."
And "Someone should
euthanize the bitch."
Yikes.
Yeah, so bring Conrad in.
People find it easier to lie
to officers in uniform,
so lock him into a statement
and pretend like you believe
everything he says.
In the meantime, we'll blow up
all his possible defenses
and alibis.
You want us to Mayberry it?
Not full-on Barney Fife,
but don't let him know
he's a suspect.
Roger.
Who's Barney Fife?
Okay, every time you ask me
a question like that...
All I hear is, "You're old."
Okay, I'm sorry, sir.
No, but really, who is he?
- Hello?
- Officer Nolan?
- It's Opal Jesper.
- Oh, hi, Mrs. Jesper.
Can you tell the reporters
outside my house to leave?
Oh, uh, no, I really can't.
But if they're trespassing,
just call 911.
I have no privacy!
- The police took my front door.
- Oh.
They probably thought there was
potential evidence on it.
Well, that's ridiculous!
What could they find?
Mrs. Jesper, look,
any questions about
the investigation
should really be directed
to Detective Harper
or Detective Lopez.
Meanwhile, I advise you stay
with friends or relatives
until things settle down
a little bit.
And now I hate to do this,
but I have to go.
I'm gonna rush you off, okay?
All right?
- All right.
- Thank you.
Okay, let's go...
where are we going?
Nolan, look.
Hello?
Mr. Bataglia?
Police!
Hello?
Control, 7-Adam-15.
We have an open door.
We're making entry
to the residence to clear it.
Mr. Bataglia!
Police department!
We're coming inside your house!
Go.
Clear!
Juarez!
The rest of the house is clear.
No sign of Bataglia.
7-Adam-15, we have a DB
at the residence.
Notify Homicide,
watch commander,
and issue a BOLO
for Conrad Bataglia.
Thanks for coming back,
Mrs. Walker,
but I just need
a little more information
before I can charge anyone.
- Anything to help my husband.
- Okay.
Now, we're hoping
to identify some
of Mr. Kalashnikov's
associates.
I mean, he couldn't have
been conducting business
all by himself
with both arms in a cast.
Um, during your dealings
with him,
did you ever see
any of these men?
Um...
him.
Yeah, it's him.
Uh, I-I-I-I think
I've seen him before.
He's involved, and he scares me.
Hm.
- Are you sure?
- I'm positive.
Listen, can you tell me
what is going on?
I've called the prison
multiple times.
No one will tell me
anything about Austin.
I'm getting worried here.
Your husband's in isolation,
where no one can get to him.
They're moving him to
a different facility tomorrow,
where he'll be safe.
What a relief.
Whew, what a relief.
Thank you, officers.
My God, thank you.
Hello?
- Austin's alive!
- What?
They have him in isolation
so no one can get to him.
They're gonna move him tomorrow.
What the hell
are you gonna do now?
- Hi.
- Stacy?
- Give me the phone.
- Wh... excuse me?
Stacy, are you there?
This is Sergeant Bradford
with the LAPD.
This whole conversation
is being recorded.
You want to save me some time
and tell me your name,
or are you gonna make me
run a trace?
Wrong number.
Trace it is.
I don't... I don't understand
what's happening right now.
You're under arrest
for the murder for hire
of your husband.
- I don't understand.
- Look, we lied.
And I'm sorry to inform you,
your husband is dead.
He was killed last night in jail
by one of Tyson's cronies.
And, look, I couldn't see
why you wanted
your husband dead until
I read his criminal history.
Again, no convictions,
but multiple phone calls
to your house
for domestic violence.
Throw in a mistress
and a judge authorized
a tap on your phone.
And you just confirmed
our suspicions.
Okay.
Oh, my goodness.
Judge just signed
the Ramey warrant for Conrad.
BOLO's in the system.
Yeah, and we put his car in SVS.
How was the wife found?
Kitchen floor,
facing the west wall.
Multiple stab wounds,
weapon still outstanding.
Well, then what, wife finds
out hubby kills Cheryl
and then confronts him?
Hubby panics and kills
the wife to silence her.
He realizes what he's done
and goes on the run.
Desperate idiot's playbook.
Uh, there are no clear prints
on the doorknob, just smudges.
What's the time element
for when she died?
Go ahead. You got this.
Well, I mean, a body loses heat
at a rate of 1.5 degrees
per hour.
Thermostat is at 68.
But the body
of the victim wasn't
that cold when we found it.
So I would say about
an hour, 90 minutes tops.
- She's right.
- Hmm.
What about the canvass?
Uh, not home, not home,
all not home.
Home, but didn't see
or hear anything.
Harper searched
Conrad's social media
and emergency contacts.
And if Conrad is running,
he's gonna need help.
So here are his closest friends.
Start from the bottom
and work your way up.
All right, I'll get
Chen's help with this.
She'll take odds,
we'll take evens.
Great.
♪ They say I'm bad
to the bone ♪
♪ Got me on the run
with the pedal to the floor ♪
♪ Pokin' at the hive,
better leave that boy alone ♪
♪ Oh, I heard
it's a problem outside ♪
♪ Man, we still tryna slide
♪ Tell me,
is you down to ride? ♪
♪ You hear that?
♪ I'm seeing blue and white
♪ I'm tryna do what's right,
uh ♪
♪ Runnin' for my life
Control, location nine
is unoccupied.
Show me en route
to location number seven.
♪ Tell me
how you figure that ♪
All right, location six,
Jose Martinez,
his husband, Todd.
It should be right up there...
By that Toyota.
Did you see that?
Yeah, I saw bushes move.
Is that Conrad?
Control, we have a possible
at location six on Brywood.
Adam-19 attach.
Conrad, I wanna see your hands.
7-Adam-15,
Code-6 on suspect Bataglia,
2300 block Brywood.
Don't move.
Show me your hands!
We got a foot pursuit,
northbound Brywood!
Come here.
Get up.
- No, wait!
- Against the car!
Aah. No! Wait!
You don't understand!
He's trying to kill me!
Hands. Hands!
Are you hurt anywhere else?
Just my head and right here.
All right, take us through
what happened, slowly.
This man broke
into our house and tied us up.
And he made me watch
while he killed...
while he killed Justine.
I don't know how I got away,
but I must have broke
the restraints.
He tried to stop me,
but I got away,
and I-I just kept running.
He's almost ready for transport.
11-79 was just reported
at 1025 South Butterfield Drive.
That's Opal's address.
Control, 7-Adam-15, you have
any more details on the 11-79?
There's a man trapped under
the homeowner's vehicle.
Fire and RA already en route.
Control, attach us to this.
Uh, Chen?
Yeah, what's up?
Would you escort Conrad
to the hospital?
- He's been Mirandized.
- Yeah, of course.
Come on.
What just happened?
Something about
the Pentagram widow.
He'll be ready to go in five.
Are they looking for him?
The guy who killed my wife?
- Can you describe him?
- I don't know.
Uh, he was white,
average height, average weight.
He was... he was deranged.
Any idea why he targeted you?
Okay, look,
I want to get this guy.
All right?
Your wife deserves justice.
But white,
average height, weight,
that's not gonna get him.
Does this have anything
to do with Cheryl Budny?
Uh...
Look,
I-I didn't mean to kill her.
I was just so tired of her lies.
We were fighting,
and I shoved her.
And I guess she hit her head.
All right, well, killing her
might have been an accident,
but carving a pentagram
into her stomach was not.
Why didn't you call the police?
I don't know.
I-I-I was scared.
I-I-I knew you guys would see
the post that I made about her.
So I tried to make it look like
it was that Pentagram guy
from the documentary.
But then today, I got a text
from Cheryl, and it said
that she wanted me to feel
the same pain that I caused.
It's on my phone. Look.
Oh!
Aah!
Officers taking fire,
2300 block of Brywood.
Shooter has a long gun.
23-31, we're 10-9-7 on Brywood.
Go.
Ready?
I'm clear!
Go!
Nobody else down Brywood!
He's got a clear shot.
Stay off Brywood.
Anybody hurt?
We're okay.
Conrad's dead.
Medic took a shot in the leg.
We can't let him escape.
We gotta seal him off.
We can't get a unit behind him.
There's a fence.
The alley doesn't go through.
- Can't they just climb over?
- Shooter will pick 'em off
as soon as they climb up.
Can I get an airship to help
seal off Brywood to the south?
Copy. Air 11 is en route.
ETA, less than three minutes.
He's gonna be gone by then.
I can get down the alleyway
and just cut him off.
No, way, that's
a 40-yard open-field run.
Well, if his head pops up,
just blow it off.
I'll be all right.
Just let me know
when you're ready.
Come on.
Go.
She made it. Code-4.
And she doesn't want
to give up her position.
Smart girl.
Stop where you are!
Stop right there!
Put your hands
where I can see them.
Turn around and put your hands
in the air.
Put your hands in the air.
Do it now.
Get your hand off your weapon.
Stop where you are.
Stop. Stop where you are.
Shooter's down!
Code-4!
I need a medic!
The shooter is down!
In a panic, the wife of
the alleged Pentagram Killer,
attempted to flee,
injuring a reporter
in the process.
...of the original spree.
Our own Steve Sahagan
was almost crushed
by the frantic widow.
Steve?
Juarez, get on crowd control.
Get these people back.
Back, folks.
Get out of the way.
Come on.
Everyone.
I need everyone to stand back!
This is a crime scene.
Opal, what happened?
I just wanted them
to leave me alone.
I thought you were gonna stay
with friends.
What friends?
I tried calling.
None of them want anything
to do with me.
It's all gone... my life,
my friends,
my home.
He took it all.
They can't blame you
if you didn't know.
Opal, did you know?
That my husband of 42 years
was a killer?
Of course not.
But there... there were some...
some things.
He'd give me jewelry
that I knew we couldn't afford.
He liked me to wear it,
and then it would disappear.
And once I-I found...
I found a pair of ladies'
underwear in the car.
I threw them away,
but I didn't ask.
I didn't want to know.
Bailey.
Hey.
I can't leave you alone
for a minute.
- I know.
- How's Carmichael? Is he okay?
Yeah, he's barely scratched.
He's going around
telling everyone
that he was shot, though.
Well, technically,
he's not wrong.
Lucy was an absolute badass
out there, though.
We're still waiting to hear
if the guy she shot's
gonna pull through.
Well, patrol found 87 guns
at that guy's house.
Looks like he finally
found a reason to use 'em.
That's unbelievable.
How's the reporter?
In surgery.
Opal crushed his leg.
What's gonna happen to her?
Well, about 50 reporters
got the whole thing on camera,
so there's not gonna be a lot
of wiggle room for the defense.
Yeah, the Pentagram Killer's
last victims.
- Hey.
- Why are you here?
- The, uh...
the Pentagram widow
ran over a reporter.
Right, right.
I passed Tim's TRAIN test.
- Congrats.
- Yeah.
I knew you would.
Didn't you have to get punched
in the face
- or something to pass?
- Oh, I did.
I mean, she was only
like 90 pounds,
but it still counts, you know.
Anyways, I came to see
if there's any news
on Lucy's shooting.
Not yet.
♪ You know I've come a long,
long way ♪
Do we know?
- Still waiting.
- Where is she?
♪ The time is caring
All right.
♪ Our hold to something
keeps us up ♪
♪ And the end is never safe
They're over there, yeah.
♪ Let it all go, go, go
Hey.
Are you hurt?
My God.
You didn't have to take my hero
suggestion so literally.
I don't feel like a hero at all.
Any news?
He's still in surgery right now.
What if he dies?
What if I killed that guy?
Then we'll deal with it.
Jeff Budny made it
through surgery.
They're taking him to the ICU.
Wait, he's alive?
Now the DA still
needs your statement
for the shooting inquiry.
And should he die
from his injuries
at a later time,
the investigation will resume.
But try not to worry
about that right now.
Can the statement wait?
Yeah, tomorrow morning's fine.
Let's go.
Come on. Come on.
Let's go home.
♪ Let it all go, go, go,
go, go, go ♪
Damn it.