Previously, on "the rookie"...
Who's this? I'll be there in 20.
- What's going on?
- I got to go.
- Just wait.
- I can't.
I'll call you when I can.
What the hell are you into
that's making you so crazy?
- I can't tell you.
- Why?
Because even knowing
about it will put you
at risk with the department.
I have a group of friends at school,
and they're getting a place together.
And I was thinking of joining them.
- You're moving?
- Kinda.
You violated procedure and
roped in two other officers?
I'm required to notify
your Metro commander.
What she does with it is up to her.
Lucy, I've been lying
to myself for a long time.
I can't just go back
to the way things were.
Are you breaking up with me?
I'm sorry.
What's happening?
I think we should have a baby.
I haven't even had a cup of coffee yet.
Maybe we table this till later?
Having a kid has been
the greatest joy in my life,
so why would I want to deny her that?
It's all about temperature.
That is the best indicator
about whether or not
I'm ovulating... that and cervical mucus.
I did not know that.
Thank you for that tidbit and for the ride.
Hey, time is not on our side.
We need to get serious
about maximizing our chances.
Agreed. Yeah.
- You let me know when the...
- Cervical mucus.
Is optimal, and I will be there.
- Morning.
Hey, you got your coffee.
I was hoping we could stop
at revolution after roll call.
We still can.
I'm gonna need four
more shots, minimum.
Ooh, bad night of sleep?
No, just still trying to get pregnant.
Poor you.
Constant sex with your gorgeous wife?
You should take a
day off to take a break.
Ok. Fair enough.
But turns out, it's not quite as much fun
when she has you on a tight schedule.
Real tight.
What time are you
getting home at today?
I couldn't say.
I'm so far behind.
Speaking of, I got to go.
Bye.
And I'll be home at my usual time.
So somewhere between
6:00 and midnight?
That's the one.
Bye, honey. I love you.
Take good care of your sister.
What the hell is a gun
doing in your purse?
It's for protection.
I have a permit.
Not in my house, you don't.
Hello, mom. Are you free today?
Because I just fired my nanny.
How did I end up with so much stuff?
I used to live out of a backpack.
Hey, listen.
If you are overwhelmed,
you could always delay
by a few days or a few weeks.
Do you need me to stay?
I mean, I know you've
been going through a lot
with the breakup.
No, no, I... no.
I wasn't saying you should stay for me.
I... I was just
you know, if you're not
ready, then you have options.
Thanks, but I am ready.
Great.
I made a reservation at
that fancy Thai restaurant
for your going-away dinner.
7:00 tonight.
I'm not going away. I'm moving 3 miles.
Girl, I am going to shower you
with love at a fancy
dinner, and that is final.
Yes, ma'am.
Did Tim really get kicked out of Metro?
Yeah.
It just goes to show, it's all downhill
after the pinnacle of you.
First day back on patrol.
Yes, sir. Yeah.
Happy to be back.
I know I have a lot of work ahead of me.
And rebuilding our trust won't be easy,
but I'm ready to do the work.
That's good to hear.
First step, I need you to take
Dr. London on a ride-along.
I'm... I'm sorry.
You asked the department
shrink to babysit me?
Well, she's not there to babysit.
She's there to observe.
You mean evaluate.
Listen, sarge, with all due respect,
I know you're... you're
worried about me, but
within the last week, you've
been bounced back to patrol
for reckless behavior,
and you broke up with your girlfriend.
Both things make me
question your judgment.
Sir, breaking up with Lucy
has nothing to do with the ray situation.
Trust me.
Listen, Tim, if you really
want to regain my trust,
this is where it starts.
Now, I can make this an official thing
and assign you mandated counseling,
which will go on your
record, or you can entertain
Dr. London for the day,
and we see where we end up.
I'll... I'll take the ride-along.
That's what I thought.
If you get into any
trouble, I'll be on patrol, too.
I'm riding with chen.
Evaluating her?
No, just observing.
Right.
You still taking bets on the breakup?
You know it.
100 bucks says Tim cheated.
You sure?
- It's running 5 to 1 against.
- Yeah.
Bigger risk, bigger reward.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I... I was never even here.
Are you taking bets
on my breakup, smitty?
No, I would nev.
"Lucy found out about Tim's secret child
"with Isabel, 5 to 1.
Lucy is sleeping with Aaron, 3 to 1."
How are the odds that
I'm cheating with Aaron,
but you know what?
That's not the point.
This is inappropriate.
I'm sorry.
You're right. I'll shut it down.
Thank you.
- Hey.
Lucy.
Ok, wait, she brought
a gun into your house?
- I know.
- With your children there?
- And you're a cop.
She knows.
Well, good luck finding a replacement.
I scheduled three nanny
interviews last week.
Two of them were hired by other families
before I could even meet with them,
and then the third one flaked.
I thought you had someone you liked.
Yeah. She can't do full-time.
And James is expanding
the community center,
so I need to find childcare in two weeks,
or Leah comes to crime scenes with me.
Any leads?
I have an interview later on today.
You want in?
Weeding through applicants together
could be a lot less painful.
Send me her background check,
and I'll start brainstorming questions.
Blair?
Dr. London? What are you doing here?
- Ride-along.
- With who?
Dr. London.
I'm sergeant Bradford.
You've signed all the waivers?
- I have.
- Great.
Officer thorsen, you're riding with us.
Great.
I mean, yes, sir.
Go get the war bags.
Yes, sir.
Interesting, bringing
Aaron along as a buffer.
Classic avoidant attachment style.
Avoidant what?
It means you prefer
surface-level relationships
to deep intimacy.
It's a defense mechanism
that can develop
when a person is
raised by an overly strict
or domineering parent.
My guess is father.
All right.
Just so we're clear, I'm not a fan
of this or therapy in general,
so don't expect me to over share.
Like I said, surface-level.
But it's not my intention to
make you feel uncomfortable.
In fact, I'm hoping we can
enjoy a nice, boring day
on patrol together.
No such thing.
I know you're worried about me, but I
I really don't need babysitting.
- It's...
- I'm not here to babysit.
You've been through a
lot... detective's exam, Tim.
I would be remiss if I
didn't check in with you.
And by check in, you mean evaluate?
Aaron, I'm... I'm hosting a going-away
dinner for Tamara tonight.
- Are you free?
- For sure.
- Count me in.
- Great.
You're also invited, sir.
Thank you.
Me and Luna have plans already.
Of course.
Are you ready?
- Yeah.
- Ok.
- Good luck.
- You, too.
I think you're right.
This definitely won't be boring.
Yeah.
Why is rent so high?
I'd say it's a complicated patchwork
of nimbyism, building restrictions,
wage stagnation.
Not helpful?
You could just wait till you
graduate from the fto program.
You'll be making a lot more money.
I just... I barely got any sleep last night.
My roommate and her boyfriend are very
vocal about their feelings.
You know, with Tamara moving out,
Lucy might need a new roommate.
- Ooh.
- No?
No, nothing.
It's just, I'd be Lucy's rebound roommate
after being dumped by Tamara and Tim.
I'm pretty sure that apartment's gonna be
an emotional minefield.
7-Adam-200.
2-73-5, your beat.
Male versus female in a
verbal, possible physical.
- Details to your box.
- You are psycho!
You left.
I thought you loved me!
- You just disappeared!
- I didn't have a choice.
- What does that even mean?
- What do you mean?
- I didn't have a...
- What's going on?
- Good, you're here.
- Arrest him.
No, what? No, ghosting is not a crime.
You didn't ghost me.
You faked your own death.
Your mom called me in tears.
Who even was that?
- My new girlfriend.
- God, I hate you!
- Hey, whoa, whoa, ok, ok.
- Whoa, that's assault.
Ok, ok.
Listen, take a breath.
As truly awful as what he did is,
and it is absolutely psychotic
he is not worth whatever revenge fantasy
you've got going on in your head, ok?
So just breathe.
I thought we were happy.
I thought he was the
one, and then it just ended.
And at least when he
was dead, it made sense.
I was sad, but it made sense.
And now I...
Well, that was fun.
- Thanks for the assist.
- Excuse me?
Ok, all right, all right. He's not worth it.
Good day, sir.
Sir, was that a setup just now?
Excuse me?
Tim just bailed on me, and our first call
involves a woman who's
literally being ghosted?
- I mean, it's...
- You watch too much reality TV.
Now, I promise you, I do not care enough
about your personal drama to hire actors
to put on a little show for you.
I'm sorry.
I do watch a little bit too much reality TV.
It's my bad.
7-Adam-15.
Missing a runaway
teenager, has been reported
at 2923 Malden in at water village.
Please respond.
- She's gone.
- Who's gone?
Emma, my babysitter.
Come on in.
I got home from work,
and my daughter was
all alone, screaming her head off.
You're sure she's not
somewhere in the house?
Yes, I looked.
She's not here, and her car's gone.
Well, did you check the nanny cam?
This is all it showed.
Ok, Chloe.
We're gonna put you in here.
Ok. I'll be back.
Has she ever done
anything like this before?
Never. She's a really good kid.
She's been babysitting for
us since Chloe was a newborn.
She wouldn't just
leave her here all alone.
Something must have happened.
- Does Emma have a record?
- No.
She's been with the
family over two years.
No drama. Always on time.
Early admission to Stanford.
A lot more squared away
than I was at her age.
So we're thinking kidnapping?
It's possible, but her car is gone.
She might have left of her own volition.
Let's hope.
We have a warrant in
process for her phone.
More units are en route.
We need you to canvass
the neighborhood.
Statements, doorbell
cameras, you know the drill.
Copy that.
Can you imagine coming
home to find your kids alone?
It makes my nanny seem
downright responsible.
Nolan just uploaded a video
from the house doorbell cam.
Ok.
That's her arriving.
What about her leaving?
That's weird.
Why wouldn't she
just use the front door?
To avoid being seen on camera.
Suggesting she didn't
want anyone to know
- she was leaving.
- Yeah, that makes sense.
I mean, she wouldn't
want the olsens knowing
she left their kid alone.
Which also means she
thought she'd be back
before anyone noticed.
Suggesting she knew the
person she was about to meet.
Stranger abductions are incredibly rare.
I mean, it's always the boyfriend, right?
Boyfriend, ex, classmate
with an unrequited crush.
Look, check with dispatch to see
if they have a list of Emma's
family and friends yet.
Breakups are a trigger for many men,
especially since
stereotypical gender roles
prevent them from seeking out help
for fear of appearing weak.
You know, I was trained
that making an assumption
about an individual based on stereotypes
is how you end up
arresting the wrong suspect.
So it looks like Bradford and thorsen
and checking out Emma's ex.
It's a good call.
You and Tim speak since the breakup?
Nope.
I thought you didn't care
about my personal life.
I mean, you don't have to
I care if it impacts the job.
Tim was a subject of an ia inquiry.
Did you two break up
around the same time?
I can't help but to wonder
if there's a connection.
Nope, it's just a bad week.
- Chen.
- Yeah?
If Tim puts you in an unethical position,
and you feel like you
have to cover for him
- no, no.
- I mean, I just
sir, it's nothing like that.
I know that the timing is weird,
but I think it's pretty simple, you know?
He's just emotionally unavailable.
The most upset I ever saw
him was when the diamondbacks
swept the Dodgers
during the division playoffs,
so that's a huge red flag, right?
I mean, that was hard to watch.
You know, I
I don't know why you brought that up.
All right, Emma was babysitting
to save up for college.
$30 an hour. Not bad.
30?
- You're kidding.
- Kids are expensive.
Get ready.
That's... ok.
We would need her 50 hours a week.
- That would be...
- That's $78,000 a year.
I can't afford that.
That is just crazy.
In my day, it was simple.
All you had to do was give
a neighborhood kid 20 bucks
and all the pizza she could eat.
Ok, no one does that anymore.
Even then, I think that
was a labor violation.
23-31, go to a backup channel.
Copy. We're 10-3 to channel 9.
How much do you pay your nanny?
With all the overtime last year,
she probably pulled down 80.
Childcare is more than my mortgage.
Ooh.
I was a nanny for a
few years after college,
and I made way more than I do now.
The thing is, we used
to be happy with sitters
who just kept a kid alive.
Now we want them to
basically have a master's degree
in childhood development
with a minor in musical theater.
I just got Emma's phone records.
This is interesting.
Her last text was from
Olivia and just says, "help."
The number is registered
to Olivia Lane, 18,
lives with her parents.
Scratch that.
Dad's in prison, has
been for seven years.
Nolan, you're closer.
- I'm sending you the address.
- All right.
We're on it.
Thanks.
What did Emma's ex have to say?
Ex?
The held hands a couple times
at a roller rink in seventh grade.
Not exactly Romeo and Juliet.
No sign of any obvious romances
on her clip talk, mostly
photos of her and Olivia.
Maybe they're the couple.
I mean, that would
explain why Emma would
drop everything for Olivia.
Could be.
Female friendships are
really intense at that age,
and a lot of romantic feelings
start out as platonic love.
You and Lucy were friends first, right?
I was her to.
Ok, you know what?
I forgot to give that kid my card.
Go run it up to him.
Yes, sir.
Hey, listen. I know what you're doing.
It's not a secret, and I
meant what I said before.
Breakups do trigger feelings of
depression and anxiety in men.
I'm not depressed.
I broke up with her.
And from what I can tell,
you're experiencing
a lot of guilt about that.
Internalizing guilt and shame
leads to self-directed anger,
even self-harm and suicide.
So you can keep
stonewalling me if you want,
but if I can't tell if you're headed down
a self-destructive path by
the end of this ride-along,
I'll have no choice but
to have you sidelined
until I can perform a
proper psychiatric evaluation.
- Everything ok?
- No.
No, the next time I send
you to do something, you run.
You just wasted valuable minutes,
which could have been
the difference between
life and death for Emma.
Good afternoon.
Coming!
That bitch make
another noise complaint?
No, we're looking for
your daughter, Olivia.
- Is she here?
- No.
What'd she do?
Her friend Emma is missing.
We think she might be in danger.
They're always at the
Olsen house, babysitting.
Right, well, they're not there,
and both their phones are offline.
I told Olivia that phone
is her responsibility.
If she doesn't pay her
bill, not my problem.
Well, do you have any idea where
the girls might have gone?
My daughter's 18.
I don't keep track of her every move.
I'm sure she'll turn up.
I'm starting to see why Olivia spent
so much time at the olsens'.
Nolan, we were able to get
into Olivia's Uber account.
Lucy and grey are checking out
the last location she was dropped.
Well, the house is a rental
overseen by a management company.
Matthew Olsen works for that company.
The dad Emma babysits for?
Yeah.
Why was Olivia coming
to his rental property?
Is this Emma's car?
All right.
Let's go up there.
LAPD. We're coming in.
Clear.
- Clear.
Hey, sarge, I got something.
So do I.
- No sign of the girls?
- No.
It feels like someone spends
a lot of time here, though.
There's takeout
containers in the garbage,
shampoo bottles in the bathroom.
Olivia ubers here twice a week.
A hook-up house.
According to the management company,
the unit is listed under repairs.
They haven't been showing
it for the last two months.
So Matthew knew he could
come and go as he pleased.
Ok.
So Matthew and Olivia
are having an affair.
She tells him that she's pregnant.
They get into a fight.
She gets scared.
She texts Emma, "help."
Emma bails on babysitting
and then gets here
and interrupts whatever was going on.
Matthew realizes if he
wants to keep his life,
he has to silence both girls.
Intimate partner violence
is the number one
cause of death of pregnant women.
And there's a gun
registered in Matthew's name.
Tracks with the blood you found.
All right. We know someone's hurt.
But until otherwise confirmed,
we have to assume both girls are alive
and counting on us to rescue them.
We need to put a bolo
out for Matthew Olsen
and bring his wife in.
Air 3's in search of suspect's car,
a 2008 silver Ford SUV,
license number 3 John Robert,
queen 1-5-8.
Your husband has been
using a vacant house
to conduct an affair with Olivia Lane.
Emma's friend?
No.
She's a child.
You're wrong.
Olivia helps out with Chloe.
She's like part of the family.
Ok, Regina, I need you to think back
on Matthew and Olivia's interactions.
You said she sometimes
helps with Chloe?
Yeah, but Matt's usually at work.
So am I.
But not always?
Sometimes Matt works from
home while Emma and Olivia
watch the baby, but he'd
ask Emma to bring Olivia
to make it less boring, like
he was doing Emma a favor,
letting her friend come over.
He'd always turn the nanny cam off.
I think I'm gonna be sick.
Right now, like detective Harper said,
we need to focus on
finding your husband.
I don't know. I don't know.
I thought he was at work.
He preyed on her, in
our house... For years.
Here you go.
I'm so sorry.
That poor woman.
Yeah.
Crap.
I forgot about the nanny interview.
She's already at the café.
See if she minds doing it on the road.
All right.
Absolutely.
Infant cpr certified.
I actually got super into first aid last year.
So yeah, I completed the red cross
wilderness training program.
So if you need someone
to treat snow blindness,
I'm your girl.
That's impressive.
And you have a bachelor of science?
Yes, my undergraduate
degree is in child psychology.
I was working on my
master's, but life got in the way.
Hablas español?
Why are you leaving
your current employer?
Well, I'm... I'm bound by an nda,
so I can't really talk about my last family,
but let's just say it wasn't a good fit.
And you can't tell us who it was for?
Sorry.
Blink once if it was a Kardashian.
This all started because of babysitting.
Babysitting.
I mean, is there anywhere
in this city that is safe?
I know you're worried
about Tamara being out there
on her own, but you should
be proud of showing that girl
that kind of unconditional love that
gave her the courage to leave.
You're right.
I guess you just have to let people go,
even the ones you care the most about.
Are we still talking about Tamara?
I just
I don't... I don't know why
this happened, you know?
And no matter how hard I
try, I can't stop thinking about it.
How... how did he let go so easily?
I really, really thought that
our relationship was worth
more than just some
cheap, cliché nonsense
about how I deserve better.
I mean, shouldn't I be the
one that decides what I deserve
and if I even want better?
Even if I wanted total self-destruction,
that is for me to decide.
It's... it's my life.
I know what you're thinking, that I was
too hard on the kid, but that's my style.
And he needs to understand
that every minute that goes by
makes it less likely
we'll find these girls alive.
You're under a lot of stress,
and not just from the case.
Whatever went down with
you and your army buddy
must have been bad for you
- to be bounced back to patrol.
- Yeah.
I own my mistakes, and I move on.
Except you haven't.
I mean, how could you
when your whole identity
is wrapped up in acting honorably?
My guess is that's
had a devastating effect
on your self-esteem, which is why
- you've been punishing yourself.
- Ok.
What... what are you talking about?
Depriving yourself of something you love
that brings you joy... or
more accurately, someone.
Ok.
So the secretary said that Matthew
never came back from
his "lunch meeting."
Of course.
His poor wife.
Hey, Bailey. What's up?
Hey, how do you feel about having sex
in the back of an ambulance?
I feel like I should maybe pull over first
and then take you off of speakerphone.
Hang on one second.
And go.
I'm just saying, the gurneys are not
as uncomfortable as they look.
Yes.
I am thinking there
may be more than one
communicable disease back there.
Yes, but my temperature is elevated.
So this is a perfect window.
Right. Right.
Not a great time for me, though.
We're looking for two missing girls.
We'll still be good tonight, though, right?
Of course. I'll see you tonight.
Excellent. Thank you.
I will see you then.
So sorry about that.
I mean, you've only
been trying for two weeks,
and she's ready for
an ambulance hookup?
Bailey does not know
how to do anything halfway.
I'm guessing she's in some
kind of contest with herself
to see how fast she can conceive.
Yeah, well, I mean, she probably knows
that the more time that
goes by, the less likely it is.
Do you know what a
geriatric pregnancy is?
If it's not ending with a
Benjamin button baby,
then probably not.
Well, it's, any pregnancy after 35.
Ouch.
All units, they flagged
an incoming 911 call
from Emma lautner.
Dispatch, can you patch that through?
Please. I'm so scared.
Where are you?
I don't know.
I got away, but... no!
Dispatch, do you
have a location on that?
Working on it.
Do you think Olivia got away, too?
I don't know.
All right. You take left.
I'll take right. Emma?
LAPD.
You here? It's safe to come out.
It's Emma.
We'll have a patrol
officer drive you home.
Cool.
I've never ridden a police car before.
That's exactly what we want to hear.
Jan, can you drive Sidney
wherever she needs to go?
Vip service.
I could get used to that.
Thanks.
- Dibs.
No, I found her.
My mom is at my house.
I need someone now.
Detectives, I discovered
the body back there.
Cleared the scene,
set up a command post.
How'd she die?
It looks like a gunshot
wound to the chest.
So she got away, but
Matthew tracked her down.
And what about Olivia?
After you've killed once,
the second time's not as hard.
If her friend Olivia is still alive,
then my guess is she
won't have much time.
See, this is a cute area.
Quiet.
Walking distance to lots of restaurants.
Possibly concealing the whereabouts
of a dangerous kidnapper?
How much is a one-bedroom?
Way out of my price range.
How much did you say
Lucy pays for her place again?
That I don't know, but I
do know it's rent-controlled.
What? How?
I'm not saying that moving
in with Lucy after a breakup
is the perfect situation, but,
but her moon is in Taurus,
which means she puts value
onto a stable home life,
even if her emotional world
is feeling out of control.
You took the words
right out of my mouth.
Sarge, I'm really sorry for dumping
all my personal business on you earlier.
I'm glad you got it all out,
but I think there's
someone else you really
want to say all that to.
All units, be advised.
Suspect's silver Ford SUV
has been identified on traffic cam
heading north on riverside
drive towards Griffith park
approximately 15 minutes ago.
Calling all units in the area to respond.
We're right around the corner.
Control, 7-Adam-100
responding and entering
the park at crystal Springs drive.
Adam-200.
We're entering on zoo drive.
Control, 7-Adam-15 responding
via Griffith park drive.
Adam-3 responding,
heading west over the old zoo.
We have additional units
inbound from the observatory.
Please stop!
- What's that?
- That's Olivia.
Please stop! Stop!
He killed Emma!
- My god.
- Olivia.
Olivia, I need you to calm down.
- Calm down.
- My god.
Where's Matthew?
I don't know.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I jumped out.
He was gonna kill me.
It's ok.
Control, this is 7-Adam-100.
We found Olivia. Send ra.
Repeat, Olivia is safe.
She's alive.
Thank god.
I don't think I could have
handled another dead girl today.
I was so scared.
I tried to end things with
him, but he wouldn't let me,
so I texted Emma for help.
And the next thing I
know, he had us tied up.
And he said for us to be together, we
we had to run away and
ok, we don't have to
talk about this right now.
All these officers need to know
is if you have any idea
where Matthew might be going.
I don't know.
But then Emma escaped, and so he,
but after she was gone, it got worse.
He was driving like a
maniac, and he had a gun.
And I thought... I thought
he was gonna kill us both,
so I jumped out.
- And I ran.
- Ok.
You're doing great, Olivia.
You're very brave.
But do you know which way he went?
There's, like, a lookout
up the hill, on the fire road.
We used to go there
to... you know, to be alone.
Air-3, suspect may be
headed to a lookout point
on northeast fire road.
Be advised, he is armed.
Copy. Heading that way.
7-Adam-15 also responding.
Hi, Olivia. I'm Bailey.
I'm here to help.
Where are you hurt?
My... my eye and my leg and my arm.
Ok.
I see that.
We're gonna have
to get you to a hospital
to make sure there's no internal injuries.
Yeah. Need anything else?
No. She did great.
We're gonna find him.
Control, I see a car that
matches the suspect's.
It looks like a silver SUV parked off
the road near water tank 76.
Copy that. We are en route.
We're five minutes away.
LAPD.
Hands in the air.
Is that
that's brain matter, and
he's got a gunshot wound
and what looks to be a
blunt force trauma wound
on the head as well.
He's in rigor.
How?
He was just seen on a traffic cam
less than 30 minutes ago.
Well, at least his car was.
Do you notice anything
unusual about that head wound?
His exit wound's too big.
It looks more like he
cracked open his skull,
and there's hardly any blood in the car.
There's no way this is where he died.
Suicide?
I doubt that.
I think he's been dead about two hours.
Which means Olivia's been lying.
She's en route to the hospital with Bailey.
We need to warn her. Olivia's a suspect.
Ra-213, this is 7-Adam-15.
You copy?
Copy, Adam-15. John, what's up?
Be advised, when you get to the hospital,
we got a 10-15.
Copy that.
Thanks for letting me know.
What does that mean, 10-15?
The police are gonna meet
us in the ambulance bay.
It's for your safety.
Look out! Look out!
What happened?
She heard Nolan on the radio,
realized something was up,
and ran into the neighborhood.
She has my knife.
Control, 7-Adam-100.
In pursuit of a Caucasian
female, Olivia Lane.
The suspect is headed
through the neighborhood
south of los feliz in blue
jeans and a pink hoodie.
Suspect is armed with a knife.
Send backup in airship.
Copy that, 7-Adam-100.
Air-3 is searching for suspect.
Airship-2 joining the search.
Heading west on lowry.
No sign of suspect.
Now we're on avocado street.
It changed names when
we crossed Rowena.
Correction.
Heading west on avocado.
Copy that.
We're headed east on
price, which just turned into,
Glen... no, wait.
Los nietos.
I hate this part of los feliz.
The street names change every block.
Adam-200 on talmage,
crossing Ben lomond place.
Did... didn't we just
cross Ben lomond drive?
Yeah.
Parked car up ahead.
Control, 7-Adam-15.
We have a possible
contact with the suspect
on the 400 block of los nietos.
Appears to be hiding
behind a blue Honda.
Olivia?
Come on.
Suspect is heading east on los nietos.
Easy. Easy, easy.
- Stay back!
- Easy.
- Ok.
- Stay back!
No, no, no, no. We're
not coming any closer.
Just put the knife down.
Olivia, there's nowhere to go.
I don't think you want to die tonight.
Come on.
Matt... Matt was the
only person who cared.
I thought he loved me.
No, Olivia, he was manipulating you.
I... when I found out I was pregnant,
I freaked out, but then... then I thought,
maybe this could be a good thing,
if I finally have someone
who loves me unconditionally.
Yeah.
But he said I was the worst
mistake he'd ever made.
Then he hit me.
I... I wasn't trying to kill him.
I don't even remember
what I hit him with.
It... it was just in my hand.
I texted Emma, and we
were gonna Bury him.
But then Emma freaked out,
and she was gonna call the cops.
And you killed her?
I panicked.
She was my best friend.
- It's ok.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Control, 7-Adam-15.
Suspect in custody.
We're at code 4.
Ok, I know I shouldn't,
but I feel bad for Olivia.
Matthew started grooming
her when she was still a minor.
This girl's got no one in
her life looking out for her.
And then this older guy starts
promising to take care of her.
And the minute she actually
needs him to, he turns on her.
I mean, that would mess anyone up.
I sympathize with her to a point,
but she did murder her
best friend in cold blood.
I feel bad for the wife.
Imagine finding out your partner
has been lying to you about everything.
That would turn your
whole world upside down.
Now she has to pick up the pieces
for both her and for her baby.
Hey, I've been thinking.
No, look, I know you and Wesley
can afford to pay Sidney
double what I can, so
I wouldn't do that to you.
If it was anyone else, I
would have hired her already.
But I have a solution
that will work nanny share.
We each pay half of her salary,
and she watches all three kids together.
I already called Sidney.
She was totally fine with it.
That is actually a great idea.
Thank you.
But since you have two young
kids, shouldn't you pay more?
Hey.
Clocking out?
Really?
You really want to pretend like
nothing is going on right now?
Have you ever thought
that maybe I have something
I want to say to you?
You were so concerned
about what I deserve.
How about a real,
adult conversation, Tim?
Lucy, I can't give you
what you're looking for.
Then you clearly have more
to figure out than I realized.
And you need somebody
else besides me
to help you with that, so good luck.
Hey, Lucy, can I... no.
- It... it can wait.
- No, what's up?
No, I... I wanted to ask you something,
- but now... now it's better to...
- It... it's fine.
It's fine. Just walk with me.
- What's going on?
- Well, I
I don't want to overstep,
but Nolan mentioned
that, Tamara might be moving out
and you might be looking
for a new roommate?
Anyway, my current living situation is
well, it... it really sucks.
And I totally understand if it's too soon.
Just thought I'd throw
it out there, just in case.
Actually, I think that's a really great idea.
You know, tonight I'm throwing
a going-away dinner for Tamara.
If you can come, you should.
And... and we can talk logistics.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Ok.
Cool.
You wanted to see me, sir?
I did.
I just got off the phone with Dr. London.
And she failed me?
No, she found you to
be incredibly insightful.
So whatever's going on with you,
she doesn't seem to think that it's
going to have a negative
impact on your work.
You sound surprised.
Yeah, I... I guess I was expecting her
to say that I have a lot
of work to do on myself.
Do you?
I think so.
What would you say if I
started seeing her as a patient?
I'd say it takes a lot of
courage to ask for help.
Look, I know you are
competitive about everything.
And it's one of the
things I... I love about you.
I'm just starting to think maybe
putting that kind of
energy on baby-making
is putting too much pressure on you
to get pregnant immediately.
Just give it some time.
It'll happen.
Even if it does, I'm
I'm worried something's gonna go wrong.
I know so many women
who have had complications
who got pregnant at my age.
And just the number of women I've taken
to the hospital is... ok,
let's not start worrying
until we have some facts, all right?
Let's start with a visit
to the doctor next week.
- Ok.
And I know this feels
like you're all on your own,
but I'm here, and we are in this together.
But make no mistake,
once you are pregnant,
you are all on your own.
Well, that's true.
It is so weird seeing it like this.
But think of all the possibilities.
I mean, you could turn this into an office,
a meditation room, a yoga studio.
Actually, I think celina is gonna move in.
Wow.
Who knew I'd be so easy to replace?
No one could replace you.
Stop it.
Look, if you ever need anything
or if you end up hating
it, you just let me know,
and I will kick celina to the curb,
like, in a heartbeat.
In a heartbeat.
I'll call you, promise.
Ok. Good.
I hope you know that you
always have a home with me.
I know.
Thank you.
Stealing your car was probably the best
decision I've ever made.
Please don't tell that story at dinner.
Ok? Please?
Fine.
I didn't expect to see you again so soon.
Yeah, I know.
I have been thinking a lot
about the things you
were saying today, and I
I think you're right.
I am mad at myself.
I can see you tomorrow morning
before your shift starts,
unless this is an emergency.
No.
Yeah, tomorrow's... tomorrow's fine.
Actually, wait.
Maybe it is.
Come on.
Damn it.