Previously on "The Rookie"...
What's all this?
I'm studying for
the detective's exam.
Monica.
She's smart, fairly ruthless,
and God forbid you leave
the toilet seat up.
Celina, look out!
It seems obvious
that they were targeted.
Bailey!
Leah!
Hi. Oh.
Angela had the baby.
It's a girl.
- Hey.
What's happening?
The list of possible
masterminds,
you were at the bottom.
Weaponizing Luke Moran
against the LAPD
has driven every cop in
the city away from our target.
By the time they realize
the damage we've done,
we'll be long gone.
Shots fired.
I am pinned down out front.
I need help.
Aaron's bleeding internally.
A surgeon must have missed
a bullet fragment.
They're rushing him
into surgery.
Is he gonna be all right?
I-I don't know.
What do I do?
Nothing you can do.
Just be there
to watch over him.
Do you guys need help?
Is there anything I can do to--
Negative. You still haven't
been cleared medically.
Celina.
We heard Aaron's back
in surgery.
Yeah, they just
rushed him in.
I, uh--I'm--
I'm on with Sergeant Grey.
Wait, you guys are
checking out already?
You just had the baby.
- It's too noisy here.
We got the pediatrician
to sign off.
We're going home.
- Unless Grey needs
something from us.
- Negative.
Just please stick
with your police escort.
I thought we caught
the mastermind, but...
now I'm not too sure.
All right, explain it to me
like I'm a toddler.
This assault was well funded
and well executed.
But Lucas Moran had
$12 in the bank
and a well-documented history
of being a loner.
We're not buying
he had the resources
to pull off the attack.
- Or the contacts.
Maybe he met someone
in prison who helped him.
Most likely, but who's
gonna spend a fortune
to kick a hornet's nest?
Who volunteers to piss off
the entire LAPD?
Somebody
with their own agenda.
Yeah, who wanted to focus
our attention on a patsy.
Divert all of our resources
to this neighborhood
so they can pull off
a new crime.
A new crime like what?
No clue.
But I'd bet my life
it's happening right now.
60 seconds ahead of schedule.
Let's keep it tight.
All right, we've been
through this a dozen times.
Cyesha and her crew meet
the inside man
and gain control
of the security room
while we take the lobby.
Then 20 minutes
to load the armored car
while Kim does her thing.
You're really not gonna
tell us what Kim's thing is?
Correct. Just focus
on your individual jobs,
and we will be made of money
by this evening.
All right, synchronize.
Three, two, one.
Mark.
Let's go.
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
Any problems?
No, they're all
in the security cage
for change of shift.
I am Glen Mercer,
U.S. Treasury Department
West Coast
Chief Security Officer.
And I'm here for an unscheduled
security inspection.
Yeah!
Grab the guns,
kill the feeds.
Hey!
- What the--
- Stop 'em!
What do I do?
Nothing.
Your part's over.
Phase One complete.
Copy that.
Moving on to Phase Two.
What?
All right.
Negative, 7-Metro-100.
There have been
no high-priority calls
in the last two hours
beside yours.
All right, dispatch,
switch gears.
I want any anomalies,
no matter how small
or seemingly random--
false alarm, noise complaint
that seems odd.
Or totally crazy--
UFO sightings, mole people.
Aside from
your earlier action,
it's a normal day in LA.
We average a dozen
bizarre calls an hour.
But none have been
from high-value targets.
Ah, come on,
there's got to be something.
Hold on.
This is a little unusual.
The Federal Reserve Bank has
an hourly check-in call
which is late.
- How late?
- 17 seconds.
That's barely a blip.
But it's all we've got
to go on.
How often are they late?
- Rarely, but it happens.
Federal Reserve is definitely
a high-value target.
All right,
I'm a few blocks from there.
I'll swing by.
I'll check it out.
We might have a problem.
Cop's outside.
7-15 on site.
Lobby's empty.
Check that.
There's blood inside.
They're robbing
the Federal Reserve.
Send backup, airship,
and an ambulance
in case of casualties.
- Time's up.
- How the hell
did the cops get
onto us so fast?
I don't know.
But we got to go.
Almost there.
- Not good enough.
- Tough.
You need to buy me
another five minutes
to get through
this last firewall.
Aisha, we need
to pivot to Plan B.
Sacrifice the lambs.
Copy.
Let's go.
Leave it!
- Let's go.
Shots fired.
I am pinned down out front.
I need help.
Duck!
Finished.
And I injected a virus
that'll make it
impossible to figure out
what we did.
Suspect's down.
He's not conscious.
Not breathing.
Appears the shot came
from the third-floor window.
They sniped their own guy.
Why would they do that?
They must have
a secondary escape route.
Didn't want to leave anyone
behind to flip on them.
The tunnels.
Let's get units rolling
to the egress points.
We don't have anybody
close by.
Harper, Nolan,
you're with me.
Shots fired,
basement hallway.
Four suspects.
Ah!
Come on.
Go, go, go, go!
- Are you nervous?
- Nope.
Last shift
before the wedding.
- Yep.
- But you're still not nervous?
Nope.
What about you?
- What about me?
- Are you nervous
that Detective Harper
will be taking over
your training in my absence?
Oh.
I--she--
When did that happen?
- Last night.
Unless you'd prefer
Sergeant Bradford.
No, no.
Well--no.
What about Smitty?
I'm kidding.
No, Detective Harper,
she's--she's great.
I mean, I'm sure I will learn
so much from her.
Not that you haven't
already taught me
everything I need to know.
Well, not that I still
don't have a lot of holes
in my training--
okay, not because
you're a bad TO.
It's--
Oh, thank God.
- What's the problem?
- My husband's missing.
He--he went out last night,
and I haven't heard from him--
Oh, no.
Officers.
Found him.
This way.
Any, um, advice
to help optimize
my experience
with Detective Harper?
- No.
- Why not?
Because so much of what we do
is dealing with the unknown.
I don't do you any service
by giving you cheat codes.
Cheat codes?
For what?
- No, nothing.
- Training with you.
Oh, there are
no cheat codes for me.
I am an enigma wrapped
in a badass riddle.
You got that, Boot?
- Yes, ma'am.
Why are you 10-8?
Uh, last shift
before I go on leave.
I know--you should be
hiding under a desk
until it is time to go home,
not out on the street.
- Why?
- The curse of the last shift.
Did nothing I taught you stick?
- Only the rational bits.
You see, Detective Harper feels
that the last shift before
a vacation, a retirement,
a wedding is to be feared.
She's very superstitious.
- I mean, so am I.
I'm riding with you.
Might as well write "collateral
damage" on my forehead.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because unlike
Detective Harper...
I do not believe
in superstitions or curses.
Today is going to be
smooth sailing.
Hey, Bailey.
What's up?
Uh, we have a huge problem.
That's great.
What's going on?
Well, the wedding planner
came by
to check her lighting setup
and somehow shorted out
the HVAC system.
It's getting hot in here.
And it's supposed to be
even hotter this weekend.
And if we don't have
air conditioning--
Okay, we will. We will.
I can fix that.
- Now?
- N-now?
Uh, yes.
No, yeah.
She probably just tripped
a breaker.
Look, we're about
to go back out on patrol,
and we'll swing by.
Okay, thank you.
Is this a huge mistake,
doing the wedding here?
No.
No, this is gonna be amazing.
Come on, best wedding ever,
I promise.
All right, I got to go.
I love you.
- Everything okay?
- Yeah.
No, perfect.
It's gonna be just, uh...
you know, just--
Juarez, let's go.
Do we have to?
I mean, there's plenty
of paperwork we could fill out.
And I'm sure Sergeant Grey
could find us things to do
at the station.
- Thanks.
- Hmm.
Hold your nerve,
Officer Juarez.
That's an order.
- Yes, sir.
Nice bike.
Thank you.
Doctor sign off
on you riding it?
You mean, like, in writing?
All I'm saying is,
is take it easy.
It's your first day back,
and you're not 100% yet.
Hell, I'm not even 100%,
and I only had a baby,
not a near-death GSW.
Yes, I will be careful,
I promise.
- Good.
- Yeah.
But the correct response
to my last sentence was,
childbirth is deeply traumatic
to a woman's body
and should never be minimized.
Right.
Got it.
So, uh, how are you feeling?
Mm, 80%.
Sad to leave my baby
but excited to use my brain
for something else.
You?
- Same--
e-except the, you know,
baby part.
Yeah, I, um--
I don't sleep well.
Too many nightmares.
But I'm hopeful that'll change
once we, uh,
catch the crew
behind my shooting.
Any fresh leads?
- Not that I know of,
but it's my first day too.
All right,
here's what we know.
The Federal Reserve heist
was a two-pronged attack.
In success,
they would have escaped
with $30 million in cash
in an armored car.
And we never would have known
about the secondary,
much larger digital heist.
While computer forensics
are ongoing,
we've so far discovered
over a hundred million
small-dollar transfers designed
to fly beneath the radar.
Any progress
on identifying the crew
that died at the scene?
- No.
- How can that be?
They were clearly
professional criminals.
No prints or DNA
in any database,
and social media scrub of
their faces turned up nothing.
Our working theory is that
a hacker sophisticated enough
to break through
the Treasury Department
firewalls
could have purged
criminal histories
from law-enforcement databases
prior to the heist.
To sum it up,
this crew orchestrated
a brutal attack on my people
in order to rob
the Federal Reserve,
killed three of their own
to slow us down,
and there's no way
to trace them
or the fortune they stole?
And given how rich
they now are,
they could be anywhere
in the world.
All right, listen up.
This crew attacked our people
in their homes,
killed six innocents.
We won't let them
get away with this.
The only way this ends
is bad guys in handcuffs.
Hey, shouldn't you be
out on patrol?
I'm stealing a few minutes
to study
for the detective's exam.
I've been slammed
with so much OT,
I've fallen way behind.
Hey, can I ride with you today
so you can quiz me
in between calls?
Yeah, sure. But it's not
gonna solve your problem.
I mean, if Lieutenant Primm
really has it out for you,
he's not gonna follow
the normal playbook
with your oral exam.
He's gonna give you
some crazy scenarios,
try and sabotage you.
- That's not fair.
The test should be the same
for everybody.
How the hell am I supposed
to study for wild cards?
You can't, I mean,
but we can spend today
chasing outside-the-box calls,
try and widen
your knowledge base a little.
Okay.
Thank you.
Don't thank me yet.
I'm not gonna make today easy.
I mean, the truth is,
you learn best
when you're
a little pissed off.
Do I?
Or are you just trying
to get me to give you
permission to be an ass?
Well, if that's
your attitude,
you really don't want my help.
- No, I do.
I-I need it.
Or do I?
I don't like that smile.
- That's my smile.
- Mm--
If you're reading into it,
that's on you.
Let's roll.
Why do I feel like
I'm making a terrible mistake?
Hey. Whoa!
It is an oven in here.
I told you.
What if you can't fix it?
- I can fix it.
Wedding is almost here.
Are you just so excited?
- Totally.
- He just blew a breaker.
I-I got a spare.
Don't worry about it.
I mean, I'm made
of anxiety inside,
but underneath that's
excitement, I think.
Well, not to make it
about me,
but I just bought a sexy dress,
and I'm ready to party.
Yes.
I fixed it
'cause I'm a genius.
And humble.
And icky.
There we go.
All right, back to work.
- To taunt the curse some more.
What curse?
Why would you say that
in front of Bailey?
- I'm sorry, sir.
- It's n--it's nothing.
It's a Harper superstition,
curse of the last shift.
I--nothing is gonna
go wrong today.
Okay?
I promise.
- Whoa.
- Hey. How can I help you?
Hi.
Yeah, uh, Josh Randall.
I just bought
the house next door.
The police.
Is--is there a problem?
Oh, no, not at all.
I'm Bailey, and this is John.
We live here.
- Oh, cool.
I've never had a cop
for a neighbor before.
Uh, anyway, I just wanted
to stop by and bring you this.
- Oh, that's so nice.
- Very sweet.
But we should be
the ones giving you
the "welcome
to the neighborhood" bottle.
Well, it's not exactly
a "welcome" bottle.
It's more of a "sorry
for the inconvenience" bottle.
I'm tearing down the house
next door this weekend,
and it's possible it might
get a little--little noisy.
- No. No, no, no, he ca--
- Okay, no, no, I--I--
I got--I got--I got it.
We're actually getting married
this weekend--here.
Yikes.
Wish I had brought
a pricier bottle of champagne.
Yeah, we're gonna
have to just
push back that demolition.
Oh, yeah, totally.
But there's no way.
Sorry, the permits have
all been pulled,
and my contractor
has a super-tight window
to get the work done,
and I'm just not able
to alter my schedule--
not not able, just, uh,
you know, not going to.
You get it.
It's what I was gonna do
and am gonna do,
but, um, anyway, I'm--
oof--just gutted
about the mix-up.
It's, um--it'll be
a fun story, right?
"Three bulldozers
at our wedding."
Anyway, see you this weekend.
Hoo.
Curse of the last shift.
I'm--I'm--I'm gonna--
I'm just--
Welcome back,
Officer Thorsen.
Thank you, sir,
and, um, thank you
for everything you did for me
while on medical leave.
You're welcome,
but that kindness stopped
when you put that uniform
back on this morning.
Sir?
I've been
where you are, son--
trying to come back
after being shot,
almost dying.
I would be doing you
no kindness
by coddling you now.
Yes, sir.
Look, I'm--I'm not looking
for any special treatment.
I'm ready to get
back on the street
and prove myself.
That's not
your decision to make.
I'm assigning you
to station duties
while you start seeing
the department psychiatrist.
Only after they approve you
for active duty
will I put you back
on the street.
Sir, with all due respect,
I'm already seeing
a pretty dope therapist.
I mean,
Lil' Gurkin swears by him.
- Who the hell is Lil' Gurkin?
- He's a--
Y-you know what?
I don't care.
The department requires you
to see their psychiatrist.
You're going.
Twice a week.
First appointment's tonight.
- There you are.
- Hey, mama.
Welcome back.
You just got a call
from BHPD.
Some guy wrapped
his half-million-dollar Lambo
around a tree in Beverly Hills.
- And I care why?
Because you had
his fingerprints flagged
in the system
with no name associated.
Hot damn.
And where is he now?
Landing at the hospital.
Why? Who is this guy?
We got a hit
on our Federal Reserve crew.
- Sir, I would like to go--
- Absolutely not.
MVA with contusions
to forehead,
possible fracture
to left humerus.
And one, two, three.
Page Dr. Hoffman.
He's gonna need
a surgical consult on his arm.
Is my Lambo okay?
It's brand-new.
I just drove it
off the lot today--
And right into a tree.
Relax.
Hello.
This is
Detective Harper, LAPD.
The man you just brought
into the hospital is wanted
for murder, armed robbery,
and assault
on law-enforcement officers.
He is extremely dangerous.
Oh!
What's the situation?
He's got a hostage in there.
She's a nurse.
I thought I had a clear shot,
but I hit her.
What kind of weapon
has he got?
It's a blade,
some kind of scalpel.
It's Lisa.
She's gut shot.
We got to get her
out of there fast.
Okay, this is gonna
be tricky.
We have no idea who this guy is
or what
his pressure points are.
We push the wrong one,
he could snap and kill her.
We don't got time
to analyze him.
I think I can get
a clean shot
if Nolan can get him focused
on the door.
If it goes sideways,
I'll take the shot.
All right, do it.
Hey, turn off the lights.
Yes, sir.
Sir, this is our first lead
in six weeks.
If he ends up dead--
Our priority is
the hostage, always.
No, yes, of course, I just--
Sir?
I'm Officer John Nolan, LAPD.
We need to talk.
About what, how screwed I am?
Or how you're gonna
offer me a ride
to a non-extradition country
if I let the hostage go?
I think we should focus on
not making matters any worse.
You both need
medical attention.
Let me get that for you.
Look, man,
you're a smart guy.
You know there's a deal
to be made if you help us.
Forget it.
I'm not a rat.
Even if I was, I'd never
survive long enough for WITSEC.
That's not true.
We can protect you.
No, you can't.
You can't.
I should never have bought
that stupid car.
He wa--he warned me.
And I'm gonna die.
But first,
I'm gonna make it hurt.
- Clear.
- Hey.
Come on!
- Keep pressure on that.
- I know.
Right.
Ready?
Come on.
There we go.
Get her out.
- What now?
- Now we hope
that the address
on his registration is real
and he left something behind
that'll lead us to his crew.
Hey, I'm gonna need your
weapon for OIS investigation.
Hey. You okay?
Better than him.
Mm.
Maybe I should have asked
Harper or Lopez
to help me study.
Eh, Harper's busy
with the task force,
and Lopez's cop brain
is just booting up.
Look, the truth is,
all ranked police officers
share the same knowledge base.
I mean, sergeant,
lieutenant, detective,
there's only about 8% unique
to each specialty.
Yeah, right, but it's that 8%
where Primm will try
and trip me up.
Maybe, but I'd argue
that's exactly
what he wants you to think.
Great.
Yeah, thank you
so much for that.
Thank you.
Now I get to play
the second-guessing game
where I spiral out of control
worrying about
whether or not Primm knows
that I think he will try
and trip me up
and that I'm focusing
on the wild cards
while he circles back
to all the stuff
I should be studying,
making me look like an idiot
at the oral exam,
pushing me so far down
the promotions list
that even if I do manage
to pass the oral exam...
oh, my gosh, I will never
even qualify for an open slot.
This is great.
Great.
Please don't.
- I didn't say anything.
I can hear you.
Y-you're thinking it.
Just--
okay, new idea--
unique scenarios
during the day,
study manual at night.
I will sleep when it's over.
- Clear.
Clear.
All right, we're gonna
have to move fast.
Any evidence our suspect
might have left behind
is gonna be useless the very
second his crew finds out
he was killed by cops.
Officer Juarez,
what is our next move?
Well, place is a rental,
clearly not the suspect's
main domicile.
So we tear the house apart
in a top-to-bottom search
while trying to avoid provoking
the curse any further.
- That's--
- Wh--uh, what curse?
It's nothing.
Last shift
before the wedding.
Yeah, I don't mess
with curses.
Not since Uncle Cheese
uncovered that ancient tomb.
You can keep your bad juju,
"Final Destination"
karma target away from me.
Okay.
Thank you.
All right, Officer Juarez,
let's start our search
in the back bedroom,
where you will recite for me
the five rules
of a domicile search
in backwards
alphabetical order.
Any mistakes you make
will result in a blue page.
If you mention the word "curse"
in my presence again,
you'll be volunteered
for all the cavity searches
at the station from now
until your 30th birthday.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Clear.
7-Metro-100.
I'm on the scene of a 187.
Assigning control
to Officer Chen.
All right, I'm here
as a resource.
But as of now,
you're in charge.
What's your first move?
Crime scene's too small.
Responding officers didn't
recover the murder weapon.
Shooter probably ditched it
somewhere along the block.
Make the call.
7-Metro-100 requesting
additional units
for an expanded crime scene,
canvass, and search grid.
Notify Homicide
and mobilize the TID team.
What else?
I mean, there's nothing else
we can do until TID gets here
to document the scene.
Am I missing something?
Do you think
you're missing something?
I think you're messing
with me.
Un--unless you're not, and
I am really missing something.
All right, well, you've
checked all the obvious boxes,
but there's a wild card.
Do you want me to tell you
what it is?
Yes. No.
Just let me think for a minute.
All right, pretend
you don't have a minute.
What are you missing?
Nothing.
Something?
What is it?
No, don't tell me.
Just--
Look, there's no shame
in not knowing
the answer, Officer Chen.
- Just let me think
for a minute,
Sergeant Bradford, please.
What is that?
The thing you should have
thought of.
No, we have to turn this off.
How are we gonna turn it off?
Ugh.
Oh, my gosh.
No.
Hey.
You need anything?
Uh, no.
The union rep is on his way,
and IA is landing in 30.
Having Grey as a witness
is a godsend.
Any one of us would have
taken the shot.
You saved Lisa's life.
I know, but I'm still gonna
have nightmares about it,
even though I've been
through it before.
Can I do anything more
to help?
Call James?
- No.
No, not yet.
I know he's gonna be mad at me
for not telling him right away,
but there's a part of him
that is gonna judge me,
and I'm just--I'm not ready
to deal with that right now.
I come bearing
burritos and babies.
Ooh, I don't know
which I'm happier to see.
Well...
- Don't judge me.
- I would never.
I heard what happened.
Sounds like a clean shoot.
- Thank you.
Aw, sweet, sweet baby.
First station visit.
That is exciting.
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
- Here you go.
Aw.
That is so cute.
Thank you.
Slow day at the front desk?
- Glacial.
- Mm.
At this point,
I'm looking forward
to department-mandated therapy.
- Mm, don't.
In-house shrinks are
a unique breed.
Most are ancient
or uninterested.
And, legally,
they don't work for you.
You got to stay vigilant.
Don't overshare.
Okay.
Uh, excuse me.
That could not have backfired
more spectacularly.
It was a literal clown show.
Hopefully nobody heard
about it.
Okay, that's very funny.
Thank you.
Hey, welcome back,
Officer Thorsen.
Thank you, sir.
It's good to be back.
It's really good to see you.
Hey, um, does everybody know
about what happened to me?
Oh, you mean the clown show?
Yeah, everyone.
Um, meanwhile, I ran
a background check
on your victim--
Claude Smith, 36,
professional clown/
mime/barista.
No priors.
Closest family's in Arizona.
And he lives right around the
corner from where he was shot.
Th-that's great.
Thank you so much.
Uh--Wesley, hey.
Sorry.
Oh, my gosh.
Um, I really need
your professional opinion.
Uh-uh.
No, I'm on paternity leave.
Oh, wait, so does that mean
you didn't hear
about my... clown show?
No, no, no, I heard.
Your crime scene was
fatally compromised.
The only way for you
to guarantee a conviction
is to get a full confession
from the killer--
that's if you can find them.
So good luck.
Great.
Sir, again, I'm--
I'm very sorry about focusing
too much on the--
the baseless superstition.
It's just in my DNA
to take these things seriously.
Okay, it's not about
taking them seriously.
It's about allowing them
to distract you.
You've been on the job
long enough to know
what can happen when you lose
focus, even for a moment.
Yes, sir.
Whoa. Sir.
Whoa.
There's only one number
in the call history.
Looks like a daily check-in
at 4:00 p.m.
That gives us
exactly two hours to figure out
what we're gonna do
the next time that phone rings.
We got a warrant
on an incoming phone call.
Audio and visual tap
of the suspect's phone.
What's that noise?
Sounds industrial.
Yeah, or mechanical.
Where's the visual?
Do we have it--
Working on it.
It takes a little longer
to activate the phone's camera.
There we go.
They're on a plane.
Yeah, it looks private.
Oh, that's a G550.
It's an older model,
2012 maybe.
You can tell that just
by looking at the ceiling?
Let's just say I, uh, spent
some quality horizontal time
on one of those
on a trip to Rome
with an Italian supermodel.
Don't judge.
- Oh, I'm judging.
Okay, so all we have to do is
figure out where they're flying
and then have law enforcement
waiting for them.
It's impossible to get
a precise location
with a phone that's flying
at 30,000 feet.
But if we can get a rough GPS
when it calls,
they might be able to match it
to the plane's transponder.
I hate to rain
on this parade,
but we don't know for sure
that our crew
is on the other end
of that phone.
It could be the hostage taker's
girlfriend,
his drug dealer.
We need confirmation
to get an arrest warrant.
We got a more immediate
problem.
That phone is gonna call
this phone in four minutes.
And whoever is on that plane
is gonna know
they're not talking
to their guy.
Unless...
Ten seconds.
Right.
Here we go.
Yo.
Wow, that thing sounds
even more obnoxious
than I thought it would.
Yeah, it kicks ass.
Where are you?
Just crossed out
of Mexican airspace.
So what'd you find out
about the place?
Banks?
Eh--it--if--ah--money.
What?
Banks, you're breaking up.
Wi--he--but--y--if--you--
eh--I--it--uh--
Think he bought it?
- We'll find out.
- Lost him?
- Yeah.
But before that,
he sounded weird.
You think something's up?
I don't know.
But better safe than sorry.
- Damn it.
- What's happening?
They destroyed the phone.
They didn't quite buy your act.
Did you connect the phone GPS
to the plane transponder?
Working on it.
Oh.
We got facial matches.
He's Boyd Taylor,
and the two women with him
are Cyesha Witt and Kim Loncar.
All have bodies on them
in connection with a previous
series of armed robberies
across four states.
- There's our confirmation.
Got the transponder.
Jet's flying
from Mexico City to LAX.
Wait, they just filed
a new flight plan
to land at Whittier.
They're pivoting in case
we're waiting for them at LAX.
Let's mount up, people.
Sir, we should really
sit this one out.
No way.
She's right.
It's your last shift.
You should stay here.
Sir, all due respect, no.
This guy ambushed my friends
and sent a killer to my house.
I need to see this through,
last shift or no.
Okay.
But you're not riding
with us.
- Sir--
- No.
What are we doing?
Thinking.
Hmm.
Feels like we're sitting.
The search of the victim's
house turned up nothing.
Family and friends gave us
no possible motives
for why someone would kill him.
And with no forensics, I--
I think I should skip
the detective's exam.
- Lucy.
- I am not ready.
No, you are ready.
Don't let Primm get
in your head.
That ship sailed
this morning.
Look, I-I know myself.
If I take this test and I fail,
it'll kill my confidence.
It's just better to wait.
Then wait.
You know, you can always work
undercover assignments
when on patrol.
So you don't believe
I can pass?
I didn't say that.
I'm just--
I'm just trying
to be supportive.
By telling me
I can't do something?
You're the one that said
you weren't ready.
N--
I-I am in a bad place.
But you just jumped right in
to amplify it.
No, I didn't.
Do you hear me?
What?
That woman in that car
was crying
while she was looking
at the murder scene.
Okay, maybe she knew him.
Or--or maybe she just had
a frustrating fight
with her girlfriend.
Police.
Show us your hands.
Uh, I-I'm not doing anything.
- Ma'am, step aside.
- Come over here.
That--that's not mine.
What about this?
Megan?
I'm guessing you tossed
the gun, didn't realize
you lost your bracelet
along with it?
I didn't mean to kill him.
He was--he was gonna tell
my husband about us.
All right, ma'am, face that
way, hands behind your back.
Ow.
- Hey, police!
- Show us your hands!
Hands up!
- Hey, freeze, lady!
Whoa! Whoa!
- Turn around, now!
- Turn around!
Nolan! Watch out!
You okay?
Uh, yeah.
Bet he believes
in curses now.
Hmm.
Help me understand
something, Boyd.
You're a Picasso
of big-money heists,
planned to the nth degree,
executed with
shocking violence.
But this job was different,
wasn't it?
Can I get a soda?
You didn't just break
into the Federal Reserve
and steal hard currency.
You hacked their computers,
got into servers
that are beyond secret.
Diet, if you have it.
Someone must have
pointed you to them,
an inside man, one that's
a hell of a lot higher up
than that security guard.
You know, I would settle
for a LaCroix--
or any sparkling water, really.
This isn't a joke--
you're gonna spend
the rest of your life
in an 8-foot cell
till they carry you out
in a 6-foot box.
Unless you come clean,
tell us who you were
working with.
Why are you questioning
my client
after he called for his lawyer?
- Nobody was asking questions.
- Well, except for me.
Seriously, can I get that soda?
I'd like to speak
to my client in private--now.
Of course.
While you're at it,
I recommend you emphasize
how tight the vise is
on his nuts.
Ooh.
Hey.
Everything go all right
with IA?
Yeah, it was fine.
It should be cleared
in the next day or so.
Good.
Well, I'm--
I'm here if you need me.
- Thanks.
- So you survived.
- Yeah.
My last shift
is officially over,
and I am still standing.
Why? Why do you insist
on tempting fate?
I think because I know
it upsets you.
Huh.
You're going to hell.
I tried everything,
but they're knocking
that house down
this weekend
during our wedding.
We're gonna have
to call it off.
No, no.
God, no.
We're not canceling
the wedding.
Well, then I'm gonna be
the only bride in history
to wear ear protection
with her wedding dress.
Yeah, that's
entirely possible.
I'm so sorry this is happening.
What's happening?
Oh, uh, just our home wedding
is a disaster,
and it's too late
to change the venue.
Oh, I mean,
you guys could get married
at my family's
spiritual oasis downtown.
Your family has
a spiritual oasis downtown?
He asked him
with great admiration.
Oh, yeah, Zen Gardens.
It's a perfect,
stylish party space.
How many guests?
both: 75.
Okay, yeah, no problem.
We can handle, like,
five times as many as that.
both: That's...
- So kind of you, Aaron.
But we couldn't ask you to--
- We couldn't?
Well, you're not asking.
I'm offering.
And it's the least I could do
for you saving my life.
Well, I didn't
save your life.
Some very talented
doctors and nurses did.
- Bailey.
- I'm just saying.
Right, but you got me
to them.
So y'all are getting married
at the Gardens,
and that's the end of that.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
- No problem.
- Now I really am gonna cry.
Yeah.
Oh, my God, thank you.
Yo, Ishani.
Hey, what's up dude   ?
This is Aaron.
It's me.
Boyd might be a problem.
Yeah, he's facing
life in prison.
If they offer him
a good-enough deal,
he's likely to take it.
Um, that kind of advice
costs extra.
100 grand.
Good.
Then my advice is simple.
You should do
whatever makes you sleep
the most soundly at night.
No, no, thank you.
Way to pull off
the fourth-quarter win.
Thanks.
What?
Nothing.
This isn't gonna work
if you're gonna lie to me.
Fine.
Did you undermine me today
because you're scared
that I'm gonna make detective?
What? No.
- Tim--
- No.
And I'm upset
you'd even think that.
Look, I don't know.
Maybe it wasn't deliberate.
Maybe it was subconscious.
So--so now you're accusing me
of being unaware of my actions?
That--that's not better.
You have to admit that
what happened with Isabel
was deeply traumatic for you.
I've never not admitted it.
I admitted it
the first day we met, okay?
So the only thing I did today
was have your back.
But i-if you can't see that,
then...
You know what?
I'm tired.
You've got studying to do.
So let's just
take the night off.
All right?
I'll see you tomorrow.
- Officer Thorsen?
- That's me.
Hi.
I'm Dr. London--uh, Blair.
I'll be working with you
if that's okay.
Yeah.
You seem awesome.
Thanks,
but the jury's still out.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't be joking.
I graduated last year,
and I've been here six months.
But I promise,
I do know what I'm doing.
Glad one of us does.
This way.
Damn it.