It was the ultimate cliffhanger.
Clifford Blossom had
killed himself. But why?
Life's not an Agatha Christie
novel. It's a lot messier.
What the hell is Cliff Blossom
doing with drugs?
Turns out,
maple syrup was a front
for his true business.
Transporting heroin from
Montreal on his trucks.
A narrative quickly emerged.
That Jason Blossom
learned about
dear old Dad's drug running,
and threatened to expose
the truth.
Which led to Jason's abduction
at the hands of a Southside
Serpent named Mustang.
And then to Jason's murder
at the hands of his father.
Clifford killed
Mustang to cover his tracks,
making it look like
he'd overdosed,
and tried to implicate
a rival businessman,
Hiram Lodge, as having
masterminded the whole thing.
And, oh, yeah,
I almost forgot.
Mr. Blossom threatened
my life,
so that my dad would confess
to pulling the trigger,
even though all he did
was clean up the mess.
Here you go, Juggy.
And he would have
gotten away with it, too,
if it wasn't for
a group of pesky kids
who uncovered the truth.
Even as Clifford Blossom,
consumed by guilt and shame,
took the coward's way out...
Jason's murder
had revealed some dark truths
none of us were
too eager to face.
Especially not Mayor McCoy,
who wanted every last vestige
of corruption crushed
like a snake
under a boot heel.
So, Blossom was the kingpin,
he funneled drugs
through Riverdale and
then shipped them out.
What the Mayor and I care
about is the local component
of Blossom's business.
Someone is selling his drugs
here in Riverdale.
- Mostly in the Southside...
- Hmm.
...but it's started to cross
the tracks, recently, too.
- And you think
it's the Serpents?
- Who else?
So here's the deal.
You feed us names,
tell me who's pushing
the dope,
and the Mayor, the DA
have a chat,
and maybe he'd be inclined
to offer you a
lesser sentence.
Serpents don't get into
the hard stuff.
It's dime bags of weed.
And I'm no snitch.
FP, if you don't help us
and your case goes to trial,
there will be no leniency.
You'll be looking at 20 years
in a federal penitentiary
for your part in the cover-up
of Jason Blossom's murder.
Dad?
You okay?
I thought I knew this town.
I bet everything on it.
If I could cut bait...
How are you holding up?
I mean, I'm...
I'm dealing.
But for Jughead and
for Betty and Veronica,
Dad, it's not over.
They're still in it. Big time.
We're all still in it.
Up to our necks.
And when should
I be expecting Mr. Lodge?
Not until the end of
the month, but everything
has to be perfect.
Yes, we would not want
to make Daddy angry.
That'll be all, Smithers.
Thank you.
He's your father, Veronica,
not the Godfather.
They're acting like
the last week and the last few
months didn't even happen.
Polly's back home,
my dad's back home,
my mom's back at The Register.
They all just keep smiling
and talking about the Jubilee.
- That's good, right?
- No.
No, it's horrible.
It's exactly the way things
were before, pretending to
be normal and perfect
when really, we're like...
Like a Greek suburban tragedy.
My family imploded, Arch,
and we barely survived.
If we don't start dealing
with our crap, it's all
gonna happen again.
Okay, Archie.
Now that we're not actively
investigating a murder case,
we need to come clean to Betty
about our pas de deux.
- What?
- Our romance.
Aw, definitely. But, Ronnie,
we have to be careful.
The last time I had this
kind of conversation with
Betty, it didn't go well.
Forget it, I'll tell her.
On top of everything else
I'm dealing with right now,
I'll tell Betty that
we're semi-dating.
Archie Andrews, Betty Cooper,
report to
the Principal's office.
Archie. Betty.
I'd like to feature you both
at the Jubilee.
As you know,
it's our 75th anniversary
of our town's founding,
and also a kickoff for
the next 75 years.
And who better represents
the future of Riverdale
than the young people
who, working with Sheriff
Keller and my office,
helped bring peace and justice
to our streets once more?
But, that's not exactly
what happened...
Let the Mayor finish,
Ms. Cooper.
Archie, the Pussycats
will be performing
at the Jubilee,
and I would love for you
to join them.
Betty, I think it's important
that we hear from Riverdale's
best and brightest.
- What do you say, both of you?
- Uh...
What about Jughead?
I, uh... I like Jughead.
And he's welcome to attend
the Jubilee, of course.
But his father is in jail,
and think it might
be confusing
to have him up
on the Jubilee stage.
That's so unfair, Mayor McCoy.
Betty, Archie, you're heroes.
The kind of heroes
that Riverdale desperately
needs right about now.
I told her I wouldn't do it.
Not unless you're
up there with us, Jug.
I appreciate the righteous
indignation, Betty, I do,
but Jubilees aren't my thing.
Jug, how's your dad?
Did you get in to see him?
Here's the latest.
Mayor McCoy wants
my dad to name names
in exchange for
a lesser sentence.
What? Whose names?
The Serpents. Sheriff Keller
thinks they're the ones
dealing the drugs that
Clifford Blossom brought
into the town.
My dad says more and more
drugs are hitting the streets.
Kevin, relax,
this isn't The Wire.
My dad says they're
not the ones dealing.
And meanwhile, Mayor McCoy
hasn't even said the words
"Clifford" or "Blossom"
in public.
It's all about how
the Serpents are the problem,
the villains.
This is outrageous.
I'm writing an article
about this,
and not just for
The Blue and Gold,
for The Register.
This is a town story.
Okay, as long as the article
doesn't include my dad.
No, it is going to be
about your dad, Jug.
It doesn't matter how many
Jubilees Mayor McCoy throws.
This town's changed.
That needs to be acknowledged.
Why are people
so afraid of the truth?
Speaking of the truth...
Archie and I wanted
to tell you...
We've kissed a couple
of times.
It's okay, Vee.
I appreciate you
being honest with me,
but I'm with Jughead now.
If you guys want
to be together,
I'm happy for you.
Thanks, Bee.
Thanks, Betty.
It was to have been
the grandest funeral
in Riverdale history.
Instead, he was buried
like a pauper.
Why are you crying?
You hated him.
Don't...
Don't say that, Mommy...
We've always been cursed
ever since the original murder
when brother killed brother.
Who will the Grim Reaper
take next? You? Me?
Maybe your father had
the right idea. Just end it.
Better the sweet hereafter
than this awful limbo.
Betty, I know you said you were
okay about me and Veronica,
but I just wanted to make
sure, because...
Because last time I said
I was okay, I wasn't.
But this time,
I promise I am.
Great.
You and Veronica, you're...
I like her, a lot.
She's amazing.
But a little part of me
always thought...
We're both so lucky.
I mean, don't you think?
To have found the people
that we were meant to be with.
And that we're all friends.
I mean,
who would have thought,
at the beginning
of the school year?
Yeah.
Who would have thought?
You wanna tell me
who those guys are out there?
Our new crew.
I let the Serpents go.
You fired them?
Why would you do that?
The Mayor and Sheriff Keller
are cracking down.
Especially on the Serpents.
Those guys stood by us, okay?
When we had no one else.
Hiram is coming home.
I can't let him,
or this project,
be associated with criminals.
You don't get to make
unilateral decisions.
'Cause we're partners,
remember?
Actually,
Hiram and I have talked,
and we'd like to buy you out.
Fred.
I've dragged you into
a situation that you never
wanted to be a part of.
Make me an offer in writing.
I'll consider it.
It's really good, Archie.
Each song, you're getting
better and better.
- That's great, Josie.
- Yeah.
'Cause I was hoping
we could...
Oh, we can't sing it
at the Jubilee.
No, my mom already
approved Astronaut.
- But my song is about...
- Your friends.
Who've been through
hell and back, I get it.
- Yeah. Exactly.
- Yeah. So...
The Jubilee, that's for
the entire town.
Not just your friends.
It's the best thing
you've ever written.
It's passionate,
it's compelling, but...
But you won't publish it.
- Why not?
- You're too involved.
People out there
are going to think
that you wrote it as a favor
to your boyfriend's dad.
No, I wrote it
because this is the truth.
It's one version
of the truth, honey.
Oh, my God. Mom.
You're just as bad
as Mayor McCoy.
We're just as bad
as this whole town.
The other reason
we don't want you
publishing this anywhere,
- is there's been reports
of attacks on the Southside.
- What?
Betty, people,
not just the police,
are going after the Serpents.
The whole town agrees
with Mayor McCoy.
Crime is spreading.
There's real anger
out there, Betty.
And they're needing
to focus it somewhere.
Right now, it's the Serpents,
and we don't want you
suddenly becoming a target.
Cheryl, I'm so sorry I'm late.
All you missed
was my abdication.
The Vixens are in the gym
awaiting you,
their new directorix.
- What?
- And I wanted
to give you this.
Your HBIC shirt?
These last few days have
put things in perspective.
I understand.
But if you personally
need anything...
I'm fine.
I've shed my tears
for the Blossom men.
It was chilling, Betty.
I'm telling you,
there are some dark
goings on at Thornhill.
Well, not just at Thornhill.
Town wide.
You can feel it. Something
wicked this way comes.
Which reminds me,
I loved your article.
Good, because
I already posted it
on the Blue and Gold's
website,
with hardcopies in circulation
tomorrow morning.
Betty, now that
it's just us girls,
and at the risk of us
failing the Bechdel test,
are you legitimately cool
with Archie and me?
Swear on the September issue?
And on my copy of Forever
by Judy Blume.
Aw, I miss this.
Gossiping, doing homework,
being a River Vixen.
Basically just going
to school.
Then come back.
Mom doesn't want me to.
Naturally, but what she
doesn't know won't hurt her.
That hottie kept
looking at you.
Hey, guys. Um...
This is Ms. Weiss
from Social Services.
She's, uh...
She's Jughead's case worker.
Jughead, I know how
terrible and emotional
the last few days
have been for you.
Your father's facing
serious jail time.
Your mom's over-extended
and out of state.
We just want to make sure
that you're taken care of.
Well, he can keep staying
with us, right, Dad?
I offered already, Arch.
Great, so what's the problem?
It was a DUI.
After your mom left.
Look, we can talk
about this later
but between that
and my cash flow problem,
it knocks me out.
There is a family on
the Southside that's
offered to foster you.
They're good people,
they've worked with us before.
That doesn't sound
completely horrible.
It does mean
you'll be in a different
school district, Jughead,
and you'll have to
transfer schools.
What the hell?
When is all this
supposed to happen?
The paperwork's
been processed.
Unless there is a radical
change in your father's case,
you'll be on the Southside
by the end of the week.
They're saying he has
to live on the Southside,
with a foster family,
and then transfer
to Southside High.
That place is no joke.
If there's a deal on
the table, Mr. Jones,
you've gotta take it.
It tears me up, Red,
but the Serpents are my tribe.
They're also innocent,
not that anyone
in this town cares.
We care, believe me.
But...
Nobody wants you
to go to jail for 20 years,
especially not Jughead.
That kid knows what's what.
He knows you can't betray
the folks that stand by you.
- Who got your back.
- And that's the Serpents?
When the time comes,
they'll step up.
Hey, Jughead's a tough kid.
Scrappy. A survivor.
He'll make it.
Especially if you're looking
after him.
And he'll try to pull
away from you,
he'll try to disappear
into himself.
He needs his friends.
That's why you and Betty,
you gotta stick with him.
No matter what.
He's got some darkness in him.
Betty's babysitting Polly,
mind if I join you?
Are you sure you want to sit
at the social pariah table?
I've been sitting at it
for months, why should
today be any different?
By the way,
I've been thinking.
You and I have a lot
in common.
Oh, because my dad's
going to prison and
your dad is getting out?
We're dating
each other's best friends,
I was going to say.
But yes,
the prison thing, too.
Jughead.
I'm sorry.
I had no right to pummel you
the way I did that day.
As recompense,
I'd like to give you this.
My iconic spider brooch.
It'll catch a pretty penny
at the local pawn shop.
Enough to keep you in burgers
and "S" T-shirts for years,
if not decades.
Cheryl, what is going on?
- I'm...
Guys, hurry.
It's Betty's locker.
Come on, it's bad.
Come on, come on!
What's going on?
Come with us.
Check it out!
Betty.
Betty. Hey, no...
It's nothing, Jug,
it's just a jerk with
a can of spray paint.
I don't think that's
spray paint, okay?
It was pig's blood, Dad.
Where do you even
get pig's blood?
I wanna slam whoever
did that through a wall.
Betty's getting threats.
Jughead is being thrown
into a snake pit,
and I can't do anything
to help them.
Sometimes you help them
just by showing up.
I've been showing up
all year, Dad.
And it hasn't made
one bit of difference.
We're getting
our asses kicked.
As long as you're with me,
you're writing articles
about me and my dad,
trouble's just gonna
keep coming at you
from all sides.
- It was just one jerk.
- It's not just one jerk.
It's Mayor McCoy.
It's Sheriff Keller.
It's Weatherbee,
it's Social Services,
it's the entire
multiverse telling me
that I don't belong here,
- so why don't I just do
everyone a favour...
- Hey, hey.
You belong here just
as much as everyone else.
This is your home.
- You know that, right?
- Yeah.
Yes.
Let me guess, for Daddy?
Veronica, wait.
You and Archie...
Getting closer?
Maybe, why do you ask?
Your father and I made
Fred an offer
to buy out the
SoDale contract,
but Fred is still
on the fence about it.
I was hoping maybe
you could talk to Archie.
Maybe he could convince
Fred to sell?
Yeah, sure, Mom. No problem.
I'll just sexually manipulate
Archie into doing my bidding.
As long as you're in control.
Oh, my God, Mom,
I was kidding.
Also, why are you trying
to push Fred out of this deal?
He's the only person
in this town who was loyal.
- Who was good to you.
- Your father is coming back.
He and Fred?
They will not get along.
- So, you took Polly to school?
- I'm so sorry, Betty.
Nothing happened at school,
it was fine.
Fine?
So, no one wrote
on your locker,
"Go to hell, Serpent Slut,"
and hung a Betty doll
from a noose?
Jeez, Poll. Is there anything
you didn't tell her?
She wouldn't stop grilling me!
I warned you, Elizabeth,
about publishing that article.
- Why do you
constantly defy me?
- Because.
I'm sick of all the secrets
and the lies in this town
and in this family.
I would much rather take
some heat for being honest
than do what you're doing.
Living in fear of the truth.
I am scared for you,
Elizabeth, not of the truth.
Oh, really?
Let's go then.
You talk a big game
about liking Jughead,
but wouldn't you
be much happier if
we weren't together?
Thought so.
Question number two,
when you invited FP
over for dinner,
he said that you and Dad
got in a huge fight
when you were in high school,
at Homecoming.
Your mom ever tell you
about that night?
Shut up, FP.
- What was that about?
- I don't know
what you're talking about.
Oh, come on, Mom.
I saw the look on your face.
You were terrified.
What were you so scared
he was going to say?
That is none of your
damn business!
Dad was keeping a secret
that almost destroyed us.
How many are you keeping?
Mommy, I was going to ask.
Can I stay at home today?
Absolutely not.
It's so hard, Mommy,
pretending everything's...
I don't care.
Here for round two?
There are some secrets
that are so painful,
you not only hide them
from the world,
but you hide them
from yourself.
What do you mean?
The night of the Homecoming,
when your father and I
were crowned King and Queen,
the fight that FP saw,
I had just told your father
that I was pregnant.
And we disagreed
on how best to handle...
Things.
And we had a really big fight.
And the next day, I went away.
To the Sisters of Quiet Mercy.
Yeah.
And five months later,
your brother was born.
The Sisters arranged
for a quiet adoption.
Oh, my God, Mom. I'm so sorry.
It's the biggest regret
of my life.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, honey.
It's okay, Mom.
The craziest thing is,
I have a secret brother
out there in the world.
It's positively Dickensian.
I love a long-lost brother.
- How old would he be?
- Mid-twenties.
Oh, my God.
A blond Adonis, no doubt.
Hey, where are you?
Have you been getting
my messages?
Oh, my God. What?
This is where I belong, okay?
Let's talk about this
after school.
Please don't worry about me.
- Where is he?
- Southside High.
He said it's
where he belongs
and that no one
wants him here.
FP warned me
Jughead would cut himself off,
go to the dark side.
Archie, we can't
let him do that.
Where would he be?
Cafeteria.
Jug...
What are you guys doing here?
I didn't tell you
ahead of time
because I knew you
would've tried to stop me.
Damn straight.
And I'm still gonna try.
Betty, the Southside is where
the powers that be want me.
Maybe I wanna
be here as well.
I may blend in better here.
And it would keep you safe.
I'm not letting Riverdale's
civil war split us apart, Jug.
They're each other's
soulmates.
Good for them,
don't you think?
Archie, what is it?
Ronnie, I...
Wait.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
Where would Cheryl go
to be with Jason?
- Sweetwater River.
- We have to go!
Guys, we have to go!
Cheryl?
She's not here.
- Over there! Oh, my God.
- She's over there!
Cheryl!
Cheryl, stop!
What are you doing?
Wait, wait! Wait, Jug!
The ice. He's right.
Too much weight,
and we'll all go under.
Cheryl!
Cheryl, please.
Just come to the shore
and we'll figure this out
together, okay?
No!
Cheryl!
- Cheryl!
The current has her.
Spread out, spread out!
She's here! She's here!
- Archie, be careful!
- Help!
Somebody help!
Archie!
Come on!
Cheryl!
Hey.
Hot chocolate?
With a little splash
of peppermint liqueur.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Are you warm enough?
What is she doing here?
She got in an accident.
And she needed help,
so I brought her here.
I'll just warm up and go home.
Fine, Ronnie.
Let's go. I'll give you
a ride to the Jubilee.
Already got one with
Archie, Lady Macbeth.
- Ready, sweetheart?
- Almost.
Don't be nervous
about your speech.
Just be your wonderful self.
It's not about
the speech, Mom.
It's Jughead.
He's moving in
with a foster family
and transferring
to Southside High.
And he says it won't change
anything between us,
but...
It will.
That's what you get
for punching a river of ice.
Are you sure you
should be performing?
Freshman year,
I played the whole season
with a broken hand.
Well, a taped-up hand.
Hey. You okay?
When we were
at Southside High,
you were looking
at Betty and Jughead...
I don't know, wistfully.
- Wistfully?
- Longingly.
Like you liked Betty.
I do. I always will.
As friends.
The moment
you're talking about,
I was seeing Betty and Jughead
and I was seeing
how good they were,
and it confirmed how I've
been feeling this last week.
I want to be that for you.
A soulmate?
A broad shoulder I can cry on
every now and then?
Yeah.
I'd love that, Archie.
Earlier,
your girl Vee, here,
called to tell me
what happened with Cheryl.
I've reconsidered something.
About your song.
Welcome, one and all,
to Riverdale's
75th anniversary
Jubilee celebration!
I couldn't be any more
thrilled to introduce
my daughter, Josie,
and her Pussycats,
as they perform alongside our
local hero, Archie Andrews!
Hi, hi, everyone.
We're switching things
up tonight.
We are singing a song
that my boy,
Archie Andrews, wrote.
So...
♪ Every moment we're together
♪ Is a moment I remember
Sheriff Keller
tells me that you still
haven't given any names.
He's hoping I can
convince you otherwise.
I've been sweating it out,
Jug, and, uh,
the only conclusion
I've come to is
that both options suck.
Hey, I wanted to
let you know that I...
I'm gonna be okay.
I met the foster family
that's taking me in.
They're nice.
What about Southside High?
It's a high school.
It's got the jocks,
and the burnouts,
and the nerds... The like.
- But I'll survive.
- You just might.
Jughead, listen to me.
I'm more innocent
than I am guilty,
but I've done some...
Some stupid things,
some bad things,
and come what may,
I have to answer for my part
of it, you understand?
I don't know what's
gonna happen when
this goes to trial,
but you need to be there
for your mom, for Jellybean.
They might not need you
right this second...
I'll do my best.
Not a doubt in my mind.
Go on.
♪ My love, my heart
♪ I wanna share it with you
♪ When it seems too hard
to bear
♪ I'll be here, I'll be there
♪ I wanna share it with you
♪ I wanna share it with you ♪
Good evening,
ladies and gentleman.
I'd like to thank Mayor McCoy
for inviting me to speak
on this historic day.
Seventy-five years
of Riverdale...
But what is Riverdale?
It's the people, right?
You, me, our friends,
our neighbors.
Riverdale is Archie Andrews.
Kevin Keller is Riverdale.
Veronica Lodge,
she's Riverdale.
But you know who else
is Riverdale?
FP Jones,
who we were so quick
to blame for Jason's murder.
Jughead Jones is Riverdale,
the very soul of Riverdale.
Without him,
we may not have ever found out
what happened to Jason.
And yet how do we thank him?
By banishing him.
Which is what we do
when the truth gets
too ugly in Riverdale.
Truth being that Clifford
Blossom was also Riverdale.
Riverdale's at a crossroads.
If we don't face the reality
of who and what we are,
if we keep lying to ourselves
and keeping secrets
from each other,
then what happened to Jason
could happen again.
Or, God forbid,
something even worse.
Riverdale must do better.
We must do better.
Fred.
Have you given any more
thought to my offer?
Yes, it is a, uh,
very generous offer.
I'm not selling, Hermione.
I... I told you,
it's in your best interest
to get out
before Hiram comes back.
Is it in your best interests?
What's best for the town?
Didn't you hear Betty?
Riverdale is at a crossroads,
and I think you are, too.
So I will see you at work,
partner.
To Archie Andrews,
who saved the cheerleader
and saved the town.
You know what, actually
I think it was Betty's speech.
Here, here to Betty Cooper.
- Cheers.
We had many
milkshakes that night,
and we all felt that as
dangerous as the world
around us had become,
here, at least in this booth,
we were safe.
Cheryl?
- Cheryl?
- In here, Mother.
What is that smell?
Gasoline.
It's the only way we can
truly start over, be purified.
Oh, God.
Wow,
it looks great in here.
I cleaned it up after
Sheriff Keller thrashed it.
Just in case my dad...
Until he gets out,
I'm not giving up on him, Jug.
Hell no.
That is why I love you, Betty.
I love you, Betty Cooper.
Jughead Jones.
I love you.
What about your mom?
At this hour, after mixing
her reds and whites
at the Jubilee,
she's no doubt
sleeping soundly in
the arms of Prince Valium.
So, come on in,
but keep it quiet, okay?
We've had this day
with each other
from the very beginning,
Archiekins.
Oh, my God.
Is that your mom?
Who else would it be?
Easy, Hot Dog. He's family.
Hey.
Heard your dad could have
named names but didn't.
Serpents take care
of their own.
We wanted you to know,
no matter what happens to him,
however long he's gone,
we've got your back.
This is yours,
if you want it.
Juggy?
Leaving without
saying goodbye?
Didn't know you were
such a scoundrel, Archiekins.
I was trying not to wake you.
My dad texted me
asking me to meet
at Pop's for breakfast,
which is what we do
when he wants to talk to me
about something serious.
- Probably me
staying out all night.
I'll call you later.
Hey, Casanova. I, uh...
I ordered you the usual.
Thanks, Dad. I'm just
gonna go wash my hands.
Who's in charge here?
Show me where the safe is!
There is no safe!
You've got a safe.
Show me where it is!
- Where's the safe, old man?
- There ain't no safe.
Show me
where the safe is!
Give me your wallet!
Imagine this instant,
frozen in time.
People will look back at this
as the exact moment
that last bit of Riverdale's
innocence finally died.
When darkness won.
Marked by an
act of violence,
that was anything but random.
Subtittle By | SupunWe |