Previously on Riverdale...
The story is about a town,
once wholesome and innocent,
now forever changed
by the mysterious murder
of Jason Blossom...
This is our insurance.
In case everything
goes to hell.
Stash it. Keep it safe.
I talked it over
with Mrs. Cooper.
She's a part of this?
She's gonna keep FP busy
while we search his trailer
to find anything
that links FP to Jason.
Or, more importantly,
FP to my dad.
We went to your
dad's trailer...
- Why would you guys do that?
- We were wrong.
We didn't find anything.
- You went behind
my back, Archie?
- Jug...
My dad just told Mayor McCoy
- about your dad.
- What about my dad?
He was just arrested.
For the murder of
Jason Blossom.
Someone planted the gun...
Jason's murder weapon,
in a closet in FP's trailer.
It wasn't there when
we searched for it.
He's being framed, Betty.
Well, maybe you didn't see it.
We're not talking about
the Vogue closet here, Bee...
Well, maybe you looked
in the wrong one.
It's a trailer
with literally one closet.
There was no lockbox. No gun.
Whatever Sheriff Keller
is saying he found,
it wasn't there.
Look, we need to tell Jughead
his dad's innocent.
Where is Jughead?
I don't know.
I tried calling him.
I left him messages.
He's not answering his phone.
In the meantime...
- Should we talk
to Sheriff Keller?
No.
Not until we tell our parents.
That we broke into
FP's trailer?
My dad will know what to do.
You did what?
We had to make sure
FP wasn't involved
in Jason's murder.
And now we know the truth.
He was.
What? Mom, no.
We just told you.
- The gun was planted.
- By whoever killed Jason.
Couldn't you have
just missed it?
Yeah, excuse me if I trust
the detection skills
of an officer of the law
over three amateur sleuths.
Mom, you're the one who
asked Veronica to break in!
- Excuse me?
- What!
- Alice?
- Actually...
I approached Mrs. Cooper.
I had to know if FP
was involved, and if he
was connected to my dad.
A gun was found.
FP is the killer.
Case closed. We're leaving.
There was no gun!
Son, this isn't
petty theft or a bar fight
we're talking about, Archie.
This is murder.
Okay, fine. Then we'll go
to the sheriff without you.
Archie, you entered
FP's residence illegally.
So whatever you did
or did not find there
would be inadmissible
in a court of law.
I don't care
what happens to me.
I do care. FP may have
ruined Jughead's life,
I'm not gonna
let him ruin yours.
Hi, Mom.
Hey, guess what?
I got a bus ticket to Toledo.
Yeah. I thought I'd come see
you and Jellybean for a while.
I could crash on the couch.
Yeah.
Mmm-hmm.
No. I...
No, I understand.
Look, I...
Forget I said anything, okay?
All right. Bye.
I changed my mind
about Toledo.
Can you just
put me on whatever
the next bus out of town is?
I don't even care
where it's going.
Citrusville, Florida.
Leaves tomorrow
morning at 6:00.
Great.
Lobby closes
in fifteen minutes,
reopens at 5:30.
Mom?
What are you looking for?
- Our passports.
- Why?
Because Lord knows
what FP is going to say,
now that he's behind bars.
So, you do think Daddy
hired him to kill Jason?
Honey, I don't know.
But, regardless of that,
we are known associates
of the man
who killed Jason Blossom.
Your father may have had
something to do with that.
Maybe not. But either way,
we need to be ready.
Ready to do what?
Run away? Like we ran away
from New York?
- We're gonna look guilty.
- Baby, we are guilty!
I'm guilty.
I bribed the Mayor
to get the drive-in land,
forged your signature,
paid off the Serpents.
If that comes out, just...
Pack a bag, okay?
Just in case.
Come on.
From what he said in the hall,
it seems like he wants to get
to his mom in Ohio.
- Anything?
- No.
Maybe his phone died.
Or maybe,
the only friends he has
just completely betrayed him.
- Is that him?
- No, it's Veronica.
Hey. You okay?
Not really.
My mom's spiraling,
and I'm on the verge.
I just wanted to talk.
Where are you?
I'm with Betty.
We're looking for Jughead.
Wait.
You and Betty went
on a manhunt without me?
I'll come meet you.
We're at the bus station,
but it's shut down
for the night.
What's the one place in town
that's open 24 hours?
Hint, we were just there.
- Told you.
- Jug.
Jug, we're so sorry...
About everything.
Juggy, we screwed up.
We all did.
Breaking into your
dad's trailer was wrong,
but at least
some good came out of it.
Pretty sure my dad was
just arrested for murder.
That gun wasn't there
when we searched his trailer.
Someone put it there
after we left.
What are you talking about?
The gun we found
in your trailer
matched the bullet
that killed Jason Blossom.
So, did you know him well,
or did you just do it
for kicks?
Last summer,
a redhead kid
comes up to me at the bar,
the Whyte Wyrm.
Said he was
planning to run away
with his pregnant girlfriend.
- Polly Cooper.
- So I would learn.
He asked me to set him up
with a getaway car
and some cash.
We made a deal.
In exchange for some wheels,
and a tidy sum, he would
make a delivery for me.
- Drugs?
- Mmm.
I got him a station wagon,
stashed some weed in the back.
Then...
I put two and two together.
Realized he was
Cliff Blossom's son.
I thought...
Kid like that has everything.
Why in the hell does he need
a guy like me?
Then he told me his plan.
On July 4th,
his sister
was going to row him
across Sweetwater River,
tip the boat,
and say he drowned.
Once he made it
across the river,
I grabbed him before
he reached his getaway car,
which he'd stashed
I don't know where.
And then,
I took him to the Wyrm...
Held him in the basement.
I kept him tied up
and worked out my plan.
Which was?
Get word to Cliff Blossom
that his son was alive,
and being held for ransom.
Set up a drop-off point
for payment to get him back.
Before I sent word to Blossom,
the kid got loose.
Tried to escape.
And that's when you shot him
and stuffed him
in the freezer.
Once things quieted down,
and your guys were done
dragging Sweetwater River
for his body,
that's when I dumped it.
The only place
we'd already looked.
You break into my house
and steal my files?
Yeah, I did.
I even followed
my son and Betty Cooper
to Jason's getaway car,
and torched it.
You must've thought
you're real smart.
Now, I wanna hear you say it.
Did you kill Jason Blossom?
Excuse me, sir.
We need to see Sheriff Keller.
There's been a huge mistake.
Sheriff, we need to
talk to you about FP Jones.
- What about him?
- He's innocent.
He's being framed.
Then why did he just confess?
Polly, the most incredible
thing has happened.
He killed Jason, not...
I went to the station.
I looked our son's killer
in the eye.
Finally, we'll have peace.
Jason will have peace.
And we...
We can all start over.
All of us.
The police report said
FP worked alone.
No mention
of your dad, Ronnie.
That's good news, right?
I can't
stop thinking that...
Maybe my dad hired
another Serpent
to plant that gun.
It's surreal, isn't it?
How's Jughead doing?
Not good.
He's not coming in today.
He's at the station.
- Being grilled by your dad.
- Who's just doing his job.
I mean, of course he's gonna
ask Jughead questions.
Okay, well,
he's wasting his time, Kev.
Because FP didn't kill Jason.
- Betty, he confessed.
- Or he was coerced.
Or he's protecting someone,
maybe a Serpent.
My mom saw him
and Joaquin together...
Don't! Do not drag
my boyfriend into this.
What're you...
- Oh, no.
- What?
What happened to him
not coming in today?
I'm sorry, Cheryl.
Enough!
Mr. Jones, you need
to come with me. Right now.
He was apologizing.
He didn't do anything wrong!
- Cheryl?
- I barely touched him.
It's not his fault, Cheryl.
Even if his dad
did do it, it's...
Everybody keeps
coming up to me,
and hugging me,
and telling me that
I must be so relieved
that my brother's killer
has finally been caught.
That this nightmare is over.
Then why doesn't it
feel that way?
What happened in there?
My second interrogation
of the day.
Don't know who's
more of a dick,
Keller or Weatherbee.
Don't listen to them.
Everyone else is wrong.
Your dad's innocent, and
we just need to prove it, Jug.
Who killed him, then, Betty?
Tell me.
If it wasn't my dad,
who killed Jason Blossom?
He said he did it,
and you know what?
I've been waiting
my whole life
for that man
to do the right thing,
and I'm done.
- You should be, too.
- Jug.
Yes, I... I appreciate it.
That was Weatherbee.
He's concerned for
Jug's personal safety.
After what happened
with Cheryl,
he's worried about the other
students' reaction to it.
Thinks Jughead should finish
the semester from home.
Jughead's getting kicked out
because Cheryl pummeled him.
How is that fair?
- It's not.
- Well, can we call, I don't
know, the school board?
Son, FP may spend
decades in prison,
potentially the rest
of his life.
We gotta think
of a long-term solution.
We are the long-term solution.
That's not how it works, okay?
I'm not his legal guardian.
Oh, good thing mom's a lawyer.
Archie, my priority
is keeping you safe.
Keep me safe
from who? Jughead?
Are you kidding me, Dad?
No, from whatever trouble
seems to follow
the Jones' around,
wherever they go,
whatever they do.
Hell, maybe you should
go to Chicago
and live with your mom.
It's not even something
I was considering, Dad.
But you know what?
Maybe I should.
Hey, if it'll keep you
out of trouble,
I'm all for it.
Hey, Jug.
I'm gonna sleep
in the garage tonight. Okay?
Jug...
Did you hear that?
Mom, what are you
doing with that?
Get behind me.
Be ready to dial 911.
Don't move.
Hands where I can see them.
Don't shoot, Alice.
- Dad!
- Hal!
These are
Sheriff Keller's files
about the Blossom
murder investigation.
How did you get these, Dad?
I broke into his house
the night
of the last drive-in,
and I took them.
Well, that's impossible.
FP Jones already
confessed to that.
Well, I have no idea
why he would do that,
because it was me.
That's why I'm here.
To destroy any evidence
that could lead back to me.
Wait, that doesn't
make any sense.
Why would FP fess up to
something he didn't even do?
Yeah, I'm not thinking
about FP right now.
I'd like to know why
your father is stealing
and destroying evidence
in a murder investigation.
Look, I was worried
that the investigation
would get back to Polly,
somehow. To us.
And somehow Sheriff Keller
would figure out
the connection
between our family
and the Blossoms.
And he would think that
there was some kind of motive.
Wait, you mean about
Great-Grandpappy Cooper
being murdered by a Blossom?
Betty...
Your great-grandfather wasn't
just murdered by a Blossom.
He was a Blossom.
After the murder,
our family severed ties
with the Blossoms
and their name,
and we took a new one.
"Cooper."
I'm...
A Blossom?
Polly is a Blossom,
which makes her and Jason
relatives by blood.
- Which is why you wanted to...
- Yeah.
Alice, that's why.
Oh, my God, Hal.
If you're willing to send
our daughter away
to keep her away from Jason...
How far would the Blossoms go
to keep them apart?
We need to get Polly
out of that house.
Don't bother calling the cops.
We're not staying. Polly!
What the hell
is going on here, Alice?
It's the middle of the night.
Oh, sorry to disrupt
the witching hour
at Thornhill.
Polly, honey, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Betty, what's going on?
We're here to bring
you home, Pol.
She's not leaving us.
She chose
to live here, remember?
With a mentally stable family.
Oh, I know all about
your family, Penelope.
- And the incest.
- What?
What incest?
Hal's grandfather wasn't
just your grandpappy's
murder victim.
They were brothers,
which made him a Blossom.
Just like Hal.
- Yeah, so what?
- "So what?"
So, everything,
starting with FP's confession,
has a few gaping holes in it.
He's being used by someone
with a crazy motive,
for example, hiding incest.
You were disgusted that
Jason and Polly were dating
because they were related.
Nothing could be
more purely Blossom
than those babies.
Okay, what is wrong
with you people?
Will you just spare us
the middle-class morality.
It's not like they were
brother and sister.
They were, what,
third cousins.
You think I killed my son?
That's it.
Polly, we are out of here.
Enough of this Doctor Moreau
experimentation in breeding
and eugenics.
It's over!
Betty, let's go.
You've made
a grave error, little girl.
No, I don't think so.
And I'm not gonna stop
until I prove it.
Juggy. Jug.
Wake up, we gotta go to Pop's.
Archie asked me to look
into your father's case.
I went down to the station,
and passed myself off
as his attorney
to try to get as much
information as I could.
How's it looking, Mom?
Well, unfortunately,
between FP's list of priors,
the anonymous tip,
and the possession
of the murder weapon...
Don't forget
that pesky confession.
Things look pretty bad.
I was with him all night,
and he never once
budged from his story.
Well, if nothing else,
at least
he's an honest murderer.
- Jug...
- Right?
Oh, also,
who is Joaquin DeSantos?
Joaquin? As in
Kevin's boyfriend?
He was FP's one phone call.
Jughead,
my advice to you is,
go and see your father.
Tell him everything
you wanna say.
Once he's arraigned,
things tend to move
pretty quickly,
and there won't be
anything left to do.
So, this might be
your last chance.
When Archie told me about
his little plan to help you,
get you on your feet,
and working with Fred,
deep down,
I knew it was a mistake.
Should have listened
to your gut.
You really had me.
Cleaning the trailer.
Convincing me that you
had quit drinking.
I was so happy,
for the first time in so long.
You paid attention to me.
Let's be honest.
The only reason
you even read my manuscript
about Jason's murder,
was to make sure
I wasn't onto you.
And you didn't want to take me
to Toledo to get the family
back together.
You wanted to get away.
You wanted to run away.
I did what I had to do!
What I always do!
Are you even sorry?
Sorry I got caught.
We done?
Look at me, Jughead!
Never come back here!
Understand?
Got it.
He called Joaquin?
Why not Jughead?
Or your dad? Or a lawyer?
- It's weird.
- What does Betty think?
She thinks it's weird.
Joaquin might know
if FP was hired to kill Jason,
if it was my father...
I need to see
this through to the end.
We know FP
used his call from jail
to get in touch with you.
What did he say?
It was basically
just a warning.
Said to lay low.
No one uses their one call
to say "lay low."
Joaquin, do you
know something?
I'm not talking to you
as your boyfriend,
I'm talking to you
as the sheriff's son.
Did FP kill Jason?
Yeah.
- I mean, I... I assume.
- Oh, my God.
Did you see him
pull the trigger?
No, no. God, no...
Then why
do you think he did it?
On July 11th,
I got a phone call
in the middle of the night
from FP.
Said he needed help
with some clean-up job
at the Whyte Wyrm.
What job?
The basement of the Whyte Wyrm
is off limits to everyone,
but that's where I met FP,
and that's where I saw...
He'd been shot.
I never asked FP
if he did it. I just...
I mean, I was terrified.
I... I just assumed.
We stashed the body
in the freezer,
cleaned up the mess,
got rid of any evidence...
You are a criminal.
Joaquin, FP has done jobs
for my dad, Hiram Lodge,
in the past.
Do you think killing Jason
was one of them?
There was one time
I overheard a conversation
between FP and Mustang...
- Who's Mustang?
- He's another Serpent.
The only other guy
who knew about the clean-up.
The guy you got
into a fight with at the Wyrm.
I heard him tell FP
something about some rich guy.
I don't know who.
- Where is Mustang?
- No, no, no, no.
You do not want to go see him.
Yes, I do.
And you're going
to take us. Or...
Or I'm going to tell my dad
about your little
clean-up job.
I'm so glad
that you're home, Pol.
And that you're safe.
And that the babies
are okay and healthy.
But God,
everything else...
Is the worst.
Betty, I saw my dad.
You were right.
He's hiding something.
Not that much money
in local crime
and villainy, huh?
This is him, here.
Mustang? You here?
Oh, my God.
- I can't... I can't be here.
- Let's go.
Call my dad.
- Son...
- I'm okay. We both are.
What were you doing here
in the first place?
We knew Mustang was a Serpent.
We just wanted to talk to him,
to see if he knew
anything about FP.
Veronica, this has to stop.
- Why are you doing this?
- Mom.
What do you think
happened in there?
Likely an overdose.
We're waiting to see
a time of death,
but it wouldn't
surprise me at all
if he was somehow involved
in Jason's murder,
and was feeling the heat.
And how'd you know
he even lived here?
Sheriff...
Found it under his bed.
Hermione Lodge?
Mind explaining to me
why your initials
are on this bag?
Not Hermione Lodge, Sheriff.
- Hiram Lodge. My dad.
- Veronica!
Mom...
He was doing business
with the Serpents.
And that's all we're saying
until there's
an attorney present.
This is exactly
what I didn't want to happen.
If you stay on this path,
you will end up dead.
Just like Jason Blossom.
You gotta believe me.
Okay? When I tell you
I'm trying to protect you.
That is my job.
It's the only one that counts.
- Do you got that?
- Yes.
Mom! Mom... Mom!
It's okay. It's okay.
You gotta tell your friends
to stop before they get hurt.
You really don't know them
at all, do you?
Just like I don't know you.
- Joaquin?
- Yeah?
I'm gonna miss you, Preppy...
Look, I didn't want
to say this
in front of your friends,
but there's something else.
My dad's been
lying to me his whole life,
but he's never been
any good at it.
I saw it in his eyes.
- He didn't do it.
- So, why lie?
Who is he protecting?
Mommy, that last morning,
before Jay-Jay
and I went to the river...
Why were he and Daddy arguing?
We've been over this.
Your father dedicated himself
to grooming Jason
to take over
the family business,
- but in the end...
- He couldn't stomach it.
When, really, I should have
been nurturing you.
Because Jason never
had the stomach for any of it.
But you... You're a Blossom.
I remember. He told me.
But why?
What couldn't he handle?
So many questions, Cheryl...
Okay, who can we rule out?
My dad.
We know why
he was acting so shady.
- Hermione.
- Yeah.
Veronica says
she's guilty of plenty,
but not murder.
Plus, she has an alibi.
She was in New York.
So, that just
leaves Hiram Lodge...
And Clifford
and Penelope Blossom...
I think something
happened, Mommy.
Whatever do you mean?
If Daddy wasn't mad at Jason
about Polly,
it must have been
about the business.
I don't know if he heard
something he shouldn't have,
or he saw something
he didn't like...
You don't know
what you're saying...
What was Jay-Jay
running away from?
The business?
Daddy?
You?
Ow!
You think
your father killed
your brother?
You think I did?
You think we murdered him
and threw him in the river,
because Jason knew
some deep, dark, horrible
secret about our business?
You want answers, Cheryl?
Are you ready?
There it is!
There's the sticky,
dark, dirty truth.
Maple syrup!
Drown in it, why don't you?
Well, what do we have here?
You two just can't leave
well enough alone, can you?
Mom, we know what
you're going to say.
The police found
another dead body.
Okay, maybe not that.
A Southside Serpent
and Sheriff Clueless
is convinced
that he was working
with your father.
He allegedly
committed suicide by overdose,
and there was
a bag of money on-site
that links him to Hiram Lodge.
Everything is tied up
into a nice little bow.
Too tidy, if you ask me.
Kevin?
Oh, okay.
We'll meet you there.
Whatever it is
we're looking for,
Joaquin didn't know
if it would help your dad,
or make things worse.
Um, guess
we're going to find out.
And why did he wait
so long to tell us?
FP called him from jail.
Told him to forget
about their plan,
some contingency plan.
He said it was too dangerous.
Deja vu.
Hey, right here.
This is meant to help FP?
I don't know. Looks like more
incriminating evidence to me.
Yeah, this just confirms
that my dad torched
Jason's getaway car.
And that his confession
was true.
Why would FP say Jason's
varsity jacket is dangerous?
What could that mean?
I can ask my father.
He would know,
considering we found
concrete proof
that he hired
the Serpents to kill Jason.
Which probably means
that your dad
pulled the trigger, Jughead.
I'm sorry.
No. No!
No, I'm not giving up yet.
Put this on.
- What?
- Put it on.
Betty, this is weird.
There's a hole in the pocket.
Okay, now we're just
grasping at straws...
Okay, no.
I don't know about you guys,
but whenever I have a hole
in my jacket pocket,
I always lose my chapstick
in the lining.
Or my Montblanc?
Hold on.
What the hell?
Nancy Drew strikes again.
Oh, my God.
Betty...
Betty, who are you calling?
You have to get out
of that house. Listen to me...
I understand.
Thank you.
Cheryl, what is it?
You did a bad thing, Daddy.
And now everyone knows.
Sheriff. Your office told me
that I would find you here.
You need to see this.
Both of you.
That night,
Sheriff Keller and Mayor McCoy
saw what we watched
in Archie's garage.
Jason, tied to a chair,
in the basement of a bar,
on the Southside
of Riverdale,
while a Serpent,
Mustang, taunted him.
Then, the unthinkable.
Oh, my God.
Later, we would learn why
my father confessed.
Because Clifford Blossom
visited him
on the night of his arrest,
with a threat,
that I, Jughead Jones,
would suffer the same fate
as Jason Blossom,
if my father didn't confess.
My dad was protecting me
from a monster,
and the nightmare
was far from over.
...charged with tampering
with evidence,
obstruction of justice,
mishandling a body,
perjury, and that's just
off the top of my head.
He's not getting out
any time soon.
I'm sorry, Mom,
that I ever thought
that Dad...
Shh, mija.
Everyone makes mistakes.
I have good news.
Very good news.
Your father's coming home.
And our families,
far from repaired...
I'm sorry, Mom,
but my friends need me.
You should come
for the summer, maybe?
That'd be great.
- You be careful.
- I will.
You better.
I love you, Archie.
I love you too, Mom.
And though
one question had been
answered that night,
that it was Clifford Blossom
who killed Jason,
a new mystery
loomed over Riverdale.
Why had he done it?
It was a question
only Clifford himself
would be able to answer.