Previously on Riverdale...
The story is about a town,
once wholesome and innocent,
now forever changed
by the mysterious murder
of Jason Blossom
on the 4th of July.
- Can we talk, Ms. Grundy?
- About what?
You're the music teacher.
Can we talk about music?
Why does she need
to leave town?
Because it's what's best.
I'll pack up my things,
I'll be gone by morning.
It's the only piece
of property in my name
and not your father's.
- Can I
get you anything?
- A job.
I can't very well have
the wife of Hiram Lodge,
on trial for fraud
and embezzlement,
balancing my books.
Oh, Hiram...
Where's the rest of it?
I saw you with that biker guy.
Your father hired
the Southside Serpents.
Nice murderboard, Dad.
Who did this?
Every town has one.
The spooky house
that all the kids avoid.
Ours was Thornhill,
the Blossom family's mansion,
with its very own graveyard.
And, trapped within its walls
like some gothic heroine,
was Cheryl Blossom.
Still grieving for her
beloved brother, Jason.
Linked in death
even as they were in life.
I told you, Cheryl.
No more sleeping
in Jason's bed.
I... I was
working on the eulogy.
- For Jay-Jay.
- Don't bother.
You won't be speaking
at his memorial.
God knows what you'd say.
Something to humiliate us?
No.
- Hey, Rocky.
- Hey.
You know, I never thought
I'd say that I miss you
playing guitar, but...
Ah. Sorry, Dad.
Just trying to get back
in fighting shape
for the field.
So, this is all for football?
Coach Clayton's about to set
the starting line-up,
name a new captain.
It's like you said.
Football gets me
a scholarship,
which gets me to college,
where I can study music.
Captains get scholarships.
This is how my dad
had his Jason Blossom
murder board
before it was trashed.
Any leads on who did that?
Or what they were looking for?
Nope. No fingerprints.
But they stole
a bunch of files,
background checks,
and all the video
and audiotapes
of police interviews.
Hey, Betty...
Trev, hi!
- Sorry to interrupt...
- Oh, no... Uh, it's okay.
- We're just, uh, working on...
- Our murder board.
Well, I just wanted to
make sure we're still
on for tomorrow?
Absolutely, it's a date.
I mean, I'll...
I'll see you there. Bye.
- So, I'll see you. Bye.
- So... Bye.
Going on a date with Trev?
Does Mama Cooper
know about that?
Kev, I'm not on house arrest.
Okay, she's out of town
at a Women in Journalism
spa retreat.
Anyway, it's not
a "date" date.
You just called it a date.
You literally said,
"It's a date."
That's just my cover.
Really, it's an intelligence
gathering mission.
We should focus on
the one thing we have access
to that your dad doesn't.
The kids at Riverdale High.
You know, maybe Trev knows
something about Jason
he didn't think was important.
Damn it!
Andrews...
What the hell was that?
Where were you, Andrews?
Because you weren't on
my field just now.
I'm sorry, Coach.
Mantle!
Sup, Coach?
You wanna be captain?
Hell yeah, I do.
Then this here is what we call
a horserace, fellas.
Now, you got a week to show me
who wants top spot more.
Good luck.
- Look, Reg...
- Save it, Andrews.
If anybody deserves
to be captain and wear
Jason's number, it's me.
Not you.
Your usual. Turkey on rye,
hold the tomatoes, to-go.
Great. Can I get
a huge cup of coffee to go?
I'm running on little
or no sleep.
Archie. Up all hours.
Listen, I was thinking maybe
we should take another stab
at going on a date.
So, what do you say?
Dinner?
Fred, um... I'm married.
And you are, too.
I'm... I'm confused here.
So, the drive-in...
That wasn't a date?
Totally my bad.
I gotta go.
Hey, Fred, wait.
It's all good.
I'll catch you later.
Betty, you're positively
radiating Nicholas Sparks.
Tell me everything
about this Trev.
Oh, there's nothing to tell.
Just one of Betty's sources,
there's nothing
romantic in the offing.
Why is everything weird here?
Why can't a date
just be a date?
What about you, Archie?
How's life in a PG world?
PG. Post-Grundy.
What, too soon?
Coach Clayton says
I have a shot at being
varsity captain.
So I'm not thinking about
anything else right now.
And you're back
to being boring.
Are you, maybe, throwing
yourself into football as
a way to avoid your feelings.
I'm not avoiding
anything, Betty,
I'm trying to get
my life back on track.
I can help with that.
I know Ms. Grundy
was tutoring you.
Understatement of the year.
But there's this
amazing songwriter
from New York,
who's an adjunct
at Carson College?
Incredible mentor.
He does some coaching
on the side
and I told him about you.
You wanna meet him?
Yeah, yeah I'd love to,
but football...
No, Archie can.
And he will.
Call him if you want,
but do it soon.
His spots fill up fast.
Thank you, Val.
Hey, now you have zero excuse
for avoiding music.
Sorry to interrupt
Sad Breakfast Club,
but I'm here to formally
invite you to Jason's memorial
at Thornhill this weekend.
To my surprise and chagrin,
mother added you
to the guest-list.
In case you're tempted
to steal our silver
candlesticks, don't.
We'll be searching bags.
Hey, try to remember,
she is burying her brother.
Cheryl, wait.
You're in pain.
This is a horrible week
for you.
I'm sure it's why
you're being
particularly obnoxious.
- Maybe. What's your point?
- Look, I don't want
to be locked
in a catfight-to-the-death
with you.
That only ends in one way.
Mutual annihilation.
- Agreed.
- So, can't we just...
Be friends?
Or, at least, frenemies?
If you really want to
extend an olive branch,
come to a sleepover
I'm having.
Fine.
Sure. When?
The night before the memorial.
I don't want to spend
the night before I bury
my brother alone.
Hi, Mr. Castillo?
Yeah, my name's
Archie Andrews.
I'm a friend of Valerie's.
Talk to me about your music.
I started writing songs
this summer, Mr. Castillo.
- Oscar.
After this kid
at my school died.
It's his...
It's his funeral this week.
Actually, the first song
I wrote was about him.
How many hours a day
do you spend writing?
At least a couple.
That's going to
have to change.
I know. And it will.
Once football season's over.
Football season?
Yeah, I play...
I play football,
is that a problem?
You tell me.
Before I sold my first song,
I was in the studio all day.
Waitering and bartending
all night.
There's no short-cuts,
unless you're a prodigy.
Definitely not a prodigy.
Do you have any songs
I can hear?
Yeah, yeah.
Where are your sheets?
Your sheet music?
I don't teach performance.
I teach song writing.
I focus on craft,
composition, lyrics.
To even talk about your songs
in a constructive way,
we need to be
on the same page.
Like, on actual pages.
Okay, I'll write out
my songs.
For tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Jason's memorial will be
held in this room.
Before he's laid to rest
in the cemetery
on Thornhill's grounds.
We've invited
everyone on our list.
What list is that?
List of suspects, of course.
People with
grudges against us,
many of them members of
Riverdale's founding families,
I'm sorry to say.
Someone in this town
killed Jason.
You know,
that's our thought, too.
Since whoever broke into
my house
knew that I'd be
at the drive-in.
Which means, there's
a very real possibility
Jason's murderer
will soon be in this room.
That's why you've invited
the Lodges and everyone else?
To investigate them?
And you think I'm manipulative
and heartless
and making this
all about myself?
I think it's great
what you guys
are doing for Jason.
You two were on the
water polo team together.
Were you guys close?
This is just us talking,
right?
Just because, I kind of
feel guilty about it.
A few months ago,
Jason started acting all,
like, weird and secretive.
Do you know why?
I thought it was about
your sister, to be honest.
They'd been dating a few weeks
when he changed.
Changed in what way?
We stopped hanging out,
he wouldn't call me back,
and then...
Then he started selling off
all his stuff.
Anything he could
sell for cash,
he was hawking.
Then I heard he was
dealing drugs...
What drugs?
Weed, pills, whatever.
I don't know for sure,
because by then
he stopped talking to me.
And all this started
after Jason and Polly
got together?
Great. Now write it down.
Musical notation. Not in tabs.
It's kind of obnoxious,
but Oscar's right.
You catch on quick, newbie.
Hey son, time to...
Uh, hey.
Hi. I, uh...
I'm... I'm his old man.
- Yeah, I'm Fred.
- Dad, this is Val.
Val, my dad.
Val. Well, it's a pleasure
to meet you, Val. Valerie.
Right,
Josie and the Pussycats.
Oh, I'm a big fan.
I... Yeah, I saw you guys
at Taste of Riverdale.
And you were rocking hard.
Thanks, Mr. Andrews.
Actually, Dad,
we're in the middle of
some music stuff, so...
Oh, right. Yeah.
I'm gonna just close this,
not all the way.
Yeah, um...
Thanks, Dad. Goodbye.
Hey, good timing.
Why don't you grab
a wrench and tighten up
that hose for me?
Dad,
every time I ask Mom
about Polly,
she shuts me down.
Can we please talk about it?
What happened?
What did Jason do
that was so bad?
Jason and Polly had a fight.
I don't know
what it was about,
but afterwards,
Polly was pretty devastated.
And I came home from work
one day and I...
I heard the water running
in the bathroom upstairs.
I went upstairs,
I knocked on the door,
I asked if Polly
was all right, and...
She didn't say anything.
So I kicked the door down.
Polly was trying to
hurt herself, Betty.
That's why we sent her away.
To stop her from trying to
take her own life again.
Betty, I'm sorry.
That's hardcore.
I asked my dad
if I could call Polly.
He said she was doing better.
But then, when she heard
about Jason's death,
she had a big setback.
He doesn't want to
risk another one.
Why does a rich kid
sell drugs?
He was running away
from his parents.
Yeah. Probably.
Or drug dealers.
Oh, my God.
Is that possible?
It's a theory.
Yours is more likely.
But why would he have
to run away from
mommy and daddy?
Because they're monsters.
Yeah, but why,
specifically.
Well, we can't exactly
just ask them.
So we have to ask Jason.
Are you proposing
a seance or...
No. Dead men tell no tales.
But their bedrooms,
their houses...
Bulldog twenty-five, on two.
- Ready?
- Break!
Red 32. Red 32.
Ready?
Hut! Hut!
Other side. Go left.
Hut!
Well done, Andrews.
Great hustle.
Ah!
- What's wrong with your hand?
- Nothing. It's fine.
- You're not playing
with a busted hand.
- I said it's fine, Reg.
Archie, sit this one out,
you'll thank me later.
Are you really
that scared of me?
Fellas, are we going to
chit-chat or we going to play?
Let's play.
Okay. Fine,
it's your funeral.
Isn't this your playing hand?
Archie.
This hand is your instrument.
You need to take
better care of it.
And, you know,
stop punishing yourself
while you're at it.
- I'm not.
- You sure?
I got slammed because
I didn't know the play.
I didn't know the play
because, like an idiot,
instead of memorizing my plays
I was up late last night.
Working on some of my songs
with Valerie.
God, I'm such an idiot.
Valerie, huh?
No, I endorse this.
You jealous, Ronnie?
Please.
I had my seven minutes
in heaven
with Archie Andrews.
Okay. Good as new.
But try to take
better care of it.
That hand is going to be
worth millions one day.
These are... fine.
I was up all night.
Yeah, I can tell.
Your sheets are
sloppy, rushed.
Okay.
I listened to your songs.
I think they're, uh, juvenile.
They're repetitive.
- They're break-up songs.
- Yeah, right.
- But Ms. Grundy said that...
- Grundy.
She was your music teacher?
One who left?
This is hard to hear,
and for me to say, but,
I think she must've...
Connected with you
in a way that I just
don't see us doing.
Wait, are you...
Is that it?
You're saying
I should just quit?
I'm saying that...
I don't think I can help you.
Thank you for having me.
Cheryl invited you.
I have no idea
why you're here.
Me neither.
I thought there'd
be other girls.
Nana Rose, would you
like some more ham?
Veronica, would you like
some more maple ham?
I'm good.
It's delicious, though.
You can really
taste the maple.
You do know that
Riverdale was founded on
the maple syrup industry.
I didn't, actually.
Fascinating.
That's where Sweetwater River
got its name.
Perhaps you should
ask your father
about it, sometime.
How is he, by the way?
Okay.
There are worse things
than prison.
Like this dinner party.
What did you say?
Hmm.
It must have been
hard for you.
Watching your father being
handcuffed and dragged
out of your home
in front of you
and your neighbors.
All those reporters.
The worst part is
how fast it happened.
He was just, gone.
I didn't even get
a chance to say goodbye.
That's why I think
it's so great.
You're all getting a chance
to say goodbye
to Jason tomorrow...
Not all of us.
That's because some people
already got to say
goodbye to Jason.
While rowing him
across the river
to his death.
Hello?
Daddy! Seriously?
- Polly?
- Dad...
Stop filming me!
Say hi to the camera, Polly.
I can't practice with you watching!
Daddy, I'm shy!
I hope this isn't weird, but
Jason was crazy handsome.
The handsomest.
Something tells me
he would've liked you.
Why did you invite me tonight?
Why not Tina? Or Ginger?
Aren't they your besties?
And yet,
that night at the pep rally,
after I had my panic attack,
you helped me.
Not them.
Cheryl.
You're allowed to say
goodbye to your brother.
- But, why does it
have to be...
- In front of people?
Yeah.
Everything with Jason's
been so...
Public. Everyone
has an opinion.
Has been gossiping.
Saying he got
what he deserved,
or that he didn't.
I just... I want everyone
to know that I'm...
I'm sorry.
And that Jason deserved a...
A better family
than what he got.
Then do it. I'll help you.
And let Penelope
and Clifford Blossom
do their worst.
Oh, they will.
They'll kill me.
I am here for you, whenever.
But why didn't you
call the cops
or animal control services?
It was a message...
...for me
from the Serpents.
I didn't call the police
because I don't trust them.
I don't trust half the people
in this damn town.
Just you.
Which is why you gotta
tell me why the Serpents...
It's Hiram.
He owes them money.
How much money?
No, Fred. That's between
Hiram and the Serpents.
Thank you so much
for coming here tonight.
But I don't want to get you
any more involved
than you already are.
You ready to enter
the belly of the beast?
It was the best I could do.
Hi.
Penelope, I just want to
offer my condolences.
Hermione, that's so kind.
Hmm.
You think you're
so clever coming here
and offering your pity?
- What are you talking about?
- So you've come to gloat?
With warmest regards
from your husband I'm sure.
You ready?
Just about.
You go ahead.
I'll be down.
Okay.
I'm so sorry for your loss,
Mrs. Blossom.
I thought you might
want to have this.
You're so much like him.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Thank you, Archibald.
Did she just touch your hair?
That was really sweet
what you did.
She deserves it.
More than I do.
Days like today really put
things in perspective, huh?
I mean, at least we're here.
At least we're alive.
Got to pace yourself, Hal.
Be very unseemly to get
a DUI on your way home.
Wouldn't you think?
- Oh, my God.
- Yes.
Welcome to Thornhill.
Thank you all for coming.
If you'll kindly
take your seats.
I'd like to start the memorial
with a few words about Jason.
You are only going
to make things worse.
The last time I saw Jason,
I was wearing this dress.
I know it's impossible.
But I swear,
when I put it on, it...
It feels like
he's in the room with me.
Even though we were twins,
I used to demand
I have my own birthday party.
Until one year,
out of the blue,
Jason convinced me we had to
combine them into one.
It wasn't until years later,
I found out why.
It was because no one
wanted to come to mine.
And Jason
didn't want me to know.
He protected me.
Every single day.
I wish, that day at the river,
I had protected him.
I'm so sorry, Jay-Jay.
We failed you. All of us.
I think we'll adjourn now
to the Winter Salon
for a light supper.
Hey.
- Hey.
- I didn't think you were
going to make it.
Yeah, I got off a little
late from work, but, um...
I did wanna pay my respects.
Yeah.
Also, I realized
something last night.
The bookkeeping position
at my company
that you applied for?
It's still open.
No snakes.
If you're interested.
Yes, yes, yes.
Um, thank you.
Yeah.
Is it me or did
the temperature just drop
like it does in horror movies?
That's just the icy chill
of the dead.
Where does a teenage boy
hide things?
Under the mattresses,
maybe in the drawers,
behind the headboard,
in the closet.
- Hello.
- Holy...
I'm so sorry,
we were just leaving.
Oh. It's you.
How lovely to see you again.
Come closer, I wanna get
a good look at you.
The horror. The horror.
Come closer, Polly dear.
It's nice to
see you again, too.
I'm sorry it had to be under
such terrible circumstances.
Well, of course
you're not wearing it.
- God bless.
- Wearing what?
The ring, Polly.
That ring has been
in the Blossom family
for generations.
You keep it close
to your heart, always.
But don't tell Penelope
I gave it to you.
Or she'll likely come and
snip it off your finger!
I won't, I promise.
Such a shame.
Your wedding
was the last thing
I was living for.
I lost a grandson,
but you,
you've lost the love
of your young life.
Poor child.
Excuse me.
I have to...
I can't...
I had to. It's what Jason
would've wanted.
No, Cheryl. As always,
it's what you wanted.
I hope you enjoyed yourself.
'Cause after tonight,
there will be
no more River Vixens.
And if not for the fact
that no one would have you,
I'd be shipping you off
to a boarding school
in Europe tonight.
What if
Ms. Grundy was lying?
People lie all the time.
Maybe she didn't want to
hurt my feelings.
Anyway, it doesn't matter.
Castillo doesn't think
I have the chops.
So, Ms. Grundy said
you were good,
and you thought
you were good?
Castillo says you are bad,
and now you think you're bad?
I just...
I want to get this right.
You wouldn't understand.
Who wouldn't? You want me
to wallow with you?
I don't have time.
You have a band
backing you up, Val.
It's not that easy...
No, Archie, it's hard.
It's almost impossible.
But let me ask you this
right now.
Who's telling you
you can't do your music?
Your coach?
Mr. Castillo? Your dad?
Or is it just you?
You dragged me out
of the Blossom house,
and then
you don't talk to me
the whole way home.
Dad, Jason and Polly
were engaged.
Did you know that?
Oh, my God.
Of course you did.
Is that what you
and Clifford Blossom
were talking about?
That is none of your business.
Yes, it is my business.
So stop avoiding it
and just tell me
what's going on.
Clifford and I were arguing
because he
and his filthy clan
came this close to
destroying our family.
Your little friend Cheryl's
great-grandfather...
...murdered yours, Betty.
Why?
The same reason
they do everything.
Greed and hate.
They were in
business together.
Selling and trading
maple syrup.
And one day
great-grandfather Blossom
decided that he didn't
want to share the profits.
So he murdered my grandfather
in cold blood.
That's why you hated Jason?
Because of some blood feud
that happened before
you were even born?
They stole our
livelihood, Betty.
And I'd die before I let them
steal my daughter, too.
- Where is she?
- She is sick!
And Jason made her sick.
And she's not coming home
until she isn't sick anymore.
Fair warning. Stay out of it.
There's not a lot of love lost
between your dad and Clifford.
Or me and Penelope,
for that matter.
Still, that family...
to lose a child that young...
That way...
I just spent the last 24 hours
in the gothic horror story
that is Cheryl Blossom's life.
And it just reminded me
how lucky I am.
To have a mom who protects me.
Then I need to tell you about
something that happened
last night at Pop's.
I saw a lot of fire and hustle
from both of you this week.
It was almost
too close to call.
Reggie, your time will come.
But for this season, at least,
this is a new number,
seeing that you took it upon
yourself to retire Jason's.
Which was the right call.
You know exactly
what a captain should
and would do.
Dude, are you insane?
Take the jersey.
I... can't.
I can't, Coach.
I love playing football,
but your starting line-up
deserves a captain whose
only love is football.
Someone like Reggie.
What?
I mean, yeah.
What? You're quitting
on me, Andrews?
No, and I really hope
you don't cut me, Coach.
Cause I friggin'
love being a Bulldog.
But that part of me that
I would have to give to you
if I were captain,
I gotta save that
for something else.
Every town has one.
The house on the haunted hill
all the kids avoid.
Now that Jason was
buried in the earth,
it would only be
a matter of time
until something
poisonous bloomed.
In that long, cold shadow
cast by his death.
Whatever grew in the rich
black soil of
the Blossom's garden
always found its way
to the town.
Whether it was murder.
Or love. Or secrets.
Or lies.
Juggie, I feel like
I don't even know
who my mom and dad
are anymore.
Betty...
if your parents
lied about Jason and Polly,
there's probably more
that they lied about.
What do you mean?
Your dad said he would do
anything to protect Polly.
So the next logical
question is...
How far would he go
to protect her?
Jughead,
whoever broke into
Sheriff Keller's house
and stole all his evidence
wasn't at the drive-in.
My Dad wasn't at the drive-in.
We need to talk to Polly.