Previously on Riverdale...
They're ruining our lives,
and to them it's just a game.
They keep score
in some secret playbook.
You want vengeance?
I'm with you.
- And I have a plan.
- You like shaming
people, Chuck?
Apologize for ruining Polly.
- What the hell?
- Do it, Jason!
- Apologize for what
you did to me!
- Look, I'm not Jason!
This is our insurance.
Here, stash it. Keep it safe.
Hermione Lodge will crumble.
Maybe you should've sent her
to jail instead of Hiram.
I heard
Mr. and Mrs. Blossom talking.
It sounded like
Clifford Blossom
was responsible
for sending
Veronica's dad to jail.
Ever since we started
dating you've ignored me,
- you've ditched me.
- Let me make it up to you.
Sorry, Archie,
but I won't be bought.
The lawyers
are coming over this week
to take our statements
for your dad's hearing.
Am I gonna have to lie?
My father is a criminal.
Weekdays,
from 8:25 a.m. to 3:01 p.m.,
we adhere to a strict regimen.
Everything in our
lives is controlled.
But then something
like the murder of
Jason Blossom happens,
and you realize
there is no such thing
as control.
There is only chaos.
Nevertheless, some of us
strive to impose
and maintain order
in what is, fundamentally,
an orderless world.
A fact which would
very soon be confirmed
in ways none of us
could have foreseen.
I'm, uh... I'm headed out.
Sorry to be missing your
birthday this weekend, Jug.
Oh, you will not be missing
anything, Mr. Andrews,
I barely acknowledge
my own birthday.
Arch, can you give me
a hand downstairs?
The good news is that
all these divorce papers
and legal mumbo jumbo
will be done.
Should be behind us
by the end of the week.
Are you only
going to see Mom now
because you
and Hermione Lodge...
No. No, son, I ended that.
Being together,
working together,
not a good idea.
In that case, then,
why finalize things
in such a final way now?
Sometimes, son, you just
gotta rip the Band-Aid off.
Or you can try and fix things.
We're past
that point, Archie.
I spoke to Mom last week,
she didn't mention
any of this, Dad.
Your mom moved out
two years ago.
She didn't tell you
because she wanted me
to be the bearer of bad news.
What if I came with you?
This is between
me and your mom.
I'll check in.
What's going on?
Veronica,
this is Paul Sowerberry,
your father's attorney.
He's here to prep us
for our statements
and help
at your dad's hearing.
Except, I told you, Mom,
I'm not giving one.
- Not one you'd want.
- Just...
You won't be asked
any questions
about your father's
business arrangements.
We just need you
and your mother
to speak to his character.
It'll humanize him.
Which could mean
a lesser sentence.
If you don't make a statement,
well, that's problematic
and damaging.
I've already told her
all of this.
Well, Dad made his bed.
And I'm late for school.
Veronica, there's something
we need to talk to you about.
Bring it.
After the morning I've had,
I'm ready for just about
anything.
Okay, well, Archie
was with the Blossoms.
While their Board
was in town, he, um...
Why don't you tell her?
You were there.
Why is this suddenly feeling
like a friendtervention?
I overheard Mr. Blossom
say he's the one responsible
for your dad being arrested
and put in jail.
Are you kidding?
Why the hell
would Clifford Blossom
have anything to do
with why he's in prison?
Hey, you may
or may not know this,
but it's Jughead's birthday.
What?
And he didn't say anything?
It's tomorrow,
and he doesn't like
making a big deal out of it.
Every year, he goes
to a double feature
at the Bijou.
It's like this tradition.
Last few years,
I've been his movie-buddy.
But now
that he has a girlfriend...
Well, of course,
I'll take him.
But you should
still come with us.
No. I don't wanna
be a third wheel.
Come on.
It'll be like old times.
The Three Musketeers.
Actually, Archie,
there were four Musketeers.
I'll see you later, Betty.
Okay.
Yeah, this is Jones.
Mr. Jones, hi,
this is Betty Cooper.
- Jughead's...
- Girlfriend, yeah, I remember.
Great, well, I'm calling
because it's Jughead's
birthday tomorrow,
and I wanted to see
if maybe you would come
see a movie with us,
maybe grab dinner?
Does he know
you're calling me?
No, I thought
maybe I'd surprise him.
Oh, man.
There's one thing
that Jughead likes less
than surprises,
and that's his birthday.
Kid's never even had a party,
never wanted one...
- What? Never?
- Mmm-hmm.
Anyway, I think the best gift
that I could give to Jughead
would be to stay away.
But I appreciate
the call, Betty.
Okay.
Anyway,
enough about my drama.
Betty, you were saying
something about Jughead's
birthday?
Yeah.
Just that Mr. Jones told me
- Jughead's never had
a birthday party.
- Mmm-hmm.
Let's have one for him.
Like, a low-key
surprise party.
- Uh, no, no.
- That's a fantastic idea.
Jughead doesn't
like his birthday.
Everybody says that,
nobody means it.
Jughead is a lone wolf.
Okay.
Ignoring the negativity.
Betty, you know me,
- any excuse to wear
a cute party dress.
- Yeah.
Okay, so I'm thinking
a quaint gathering,
inner-circle only.
Oh, my God,
don't turn around.
Holy Chuck,
I think his lats got bigger.
Not that I care,
because he's evil incarnate.
What's Chuck Clayton
doing back?
He got suspended,
not expelled.
Even though he should
have been drawn and quartered
for what he did.
Oh, my God.
Get away from her, Chuck.
Easy. Look, I only came
over here to apologize.
You don't have to go
Dark Betty on me again.
I'm not going!
I'm not going Dark anything.
Ethel, is Chuck bothering you?
You can relax,
Betty, it's fine.
Yeah, Betty, we're fine.
The real question is, are you?
What was he doing?
Accosting her?
No, he was... Apologizing.
Oh, I'm so sure.
Chuck Clayton doesn't have
a contrite bone in his
muscle-bound body.
You know what, can we talk
about something else?
Like... Like Jughead's
surprise party.
Betty?
Look,
there's a lot I can't do,
a lot I can't control.
But I can damn well make sure
my boyfriend has the best
birthday of his life.
Screw it. I'm with Betty.
My dad's away.
We can do it at my house.
We could all use a good time.
Now you're talking
my language.
It's gonna be epic.
Mr. Jones,
I didn't mean to ambush you.
I know you don't do birthdays,
but Archie and I are having
a few of Jughead's friends
over at Archie's house.
And I bet it would mean
so much to Jughead
if you came.
- Man, you don't quit, do you?
- Rarely, if ever.
I really wanna do
something special for him.
And you being there...
That would be special.
Great news, Betty.
I just had a terrific meeting
with Principal Weatherbee,
who agrees
that the Blue and Gold
can benefit greatly
from my professional guidance
- as your new advisor.
- That's great, Mom.
So what are we working on?
A list of supplies
for Jughead's birthday party.
You're really falling
for this Jones boy,
aren't you?
Mom, when you and Dad
started dating,
did you tell him everything
about yourself?
I sure did,
and I wish I hadn't.
I shared things
with your father,
my secrets, fears, doubts.
And he ended up
using them against me.
What secrets?
Let's just say
that there are some things
about myself that
I struggle with.
I trust Jughead, Mom.
Of course you do.
And you should.
But just not with everything.
So... A John Landis
double feature at the Bijou.
American Werewolf in London
and Animal House.
That's awesome. Except...
You're going
with Betty instead.
You told her
about my birthday?
Dude, come on.
That's a primal betrayal.
Why do you hate
your birthday so much, Jug?
PTSD from when I was a kid.
I don't know.
Things were always
messed up at home.
Usually because of my dad.
And then there was
this arbitrary day,
that we would
just get together and
pretend things were great,
we were normal.
And it just made me feel
really lonely.
What's all this?
Dad's files
from the basement, Mom.
Archie overheard Mr. Blossom
say that he's the one
responsible
for putting Dad in jail.
So I did some digging.
And found this spreadsheet
of monthly payments
from Blossom Maple Farms
to Lodge Industries
until about five months ago,
when they stopped.
When your father was arrested.
There's more.
The payments,
which are significant,
by the way,
have been happening
for 75 years.
That's a ton of money.
What if Clifford
implicated Daddy
to get out of paying
the monthly fee?
I wouldn't put it past
the wig-wearing monster.
- We should tell Dad's lawyers.
- Well, hold on.
If Clifford did orchestrate
your father's arrest,
people might think
that Hiram had something to do
with Jason Blossom's murder.
Ronnie?
You got to let this go.
You don't think Dad could,
in any way,
be responsible for Jason's
murder, do you?
No, honey, look,
don't make things worse
by asking questions
that no one else is asking.
And please, God, do not
bring the Blossoms into this.
And that includes Cheryl.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four... Stop.
You're late, Veronica,
we've already reviewed
the new choreography
for Homecoming.
That means
you'll be in the back,
where your presence
will do the least
amount of damage.
With you front and center,
no doubt.
But of course.
I do have the maddest skills
on this squad.
And because you're a Blossom,
we have to accept whatever
you say as gospel truth?
You're welcome
to challenge me, Veronica,
but you'll lose.
We live in a democratic
society, Cheryl.
Let's let the Vixens decide
who's cherry on top.
- Challenge accepted.
- Great.
All those for Cheryl?
All those for Veronica?
Never cross a Lodge.
Come on, girls.
You catatonic bimbos
didn't even vote.
So you stuttering sapheads
are too dim to exercise
your own rights,
and you've got the combined
vocabulary of a baked potato.
Consider this your last
practice as River Vixens,
and your last week
as my social handmaidens.
You're fired on all fronts.
That's all. Shoo, bitches.
- Hey, Dad, what's up?
- Just checking in.
I felt bad we didn't
get the chance to talk more
before I left.
Yeah, well, you kind
of shut me down, Dad.
You seen Mom yet?
No. We were gonna
have dinner, but...
- But what?
- We decided it would be better
to meet tomorrow morning,
with the lawyers.
Right.
'Cause things are so bad,
you can't talk
without a mediator.
Dad, I gotta go, bye.
Okay, so you're the worst.
But it just so happens
that both our archnemesi,
Betty Cooper
and Veronica Lodge,
will be at a little shindig
at that chowderhead
Archie's house.
Wanna team-up for a little
destruction, Chuck?
Mr. Sowerberry,
let me tell you
what I think happened.
The Blossoms agreed to pay
my family a fee in perpetuity.
Clifford Blossom
tried to end this agreement
so he could stop
paying my family
after all these decades.
And when my father,
being my father, refused,
it was Clifford
who called the police
and got him arrested.
That's what I'm thinking.
I can't confirm or deny...
And the reason
this hasn't come out yet
is because it might
make my Dad look
like a murder suspect?
That is our concern, yes.
Have you changed your mind
about making a statement?
If anything,
I'm less inclined.
I told your father
that you were...
Conflicted about helping him.
"My darling daughter.
"If you do not testify
on my behalf,
"I'm afraid your poor mother
might be drawn
into this awful mess.
"It pains me to say,
but she is not nearly
as innocent as you believe.
"Think carefully about
your next move, Veronica.
"The rest of your life,
and your mother's,
"will be decided by it."
Hey,
I was talking to Kevin.
He told me
that you and Chuck
had some scene
in the cafeteria yesterday.
It wasn't a big deal.
What exactly happened
between you guys that night?
Veronica asked me to keep
the details under wraps, okay?
Yeah. All right. No worries.
I only really asked
because you made it sound
like you were upset.
If I was upset about anything,
it was that I had to hear
about your birthday
from Archie and not you, Jug.
Yeah, well...
I didn't think you were
an American Werewolf
kind of girl.
Ooh. That's where
you're wrong, Jughead Jones.
I'm all about
the beast within.
If it's a double feature,
does that mean I have time
to go to the bathroom?
I'd hold it, Ethel.
Surprise!
Do I look like Jughead to you?
Oh. Betty just texted me.
They're almost here.
You've met Joaquin, right?
I haven't had the pleasure.
Also I thought
it was inner-circle only
tonight?
Joaquin's my boyfriend,
that makes him inner-circle.
Uh-huh, well, I just came
from the most insane meeting
with my dad's lawyer.
Between his upcoming hearing
and his potential involvement
in Jason's murder,
not to mention my mom's,
I'm in a foul mood.
Guys, they're really coming
this time.
Everybody hide.
Ugh, I'm so over this.
Surprise!
This is why we left
the double feature.
Happy birthday, bro.
You really shouldn't have.
Ugh, you reek. Are you drunk?
No.
Thanks, Veronica.
Thanks, everyone.
- Oh, it's Kevin!
- Happy birthday, bud.
This is my boyfriend,
Joaquin.
Hey, nice to meet you.
Um, has anyone seen Betty?
That was haunting, Betty.
Blow out the candles
and make a wish.
I wish it were just
the two of us right now.
One blow!
Veronica?
The stuff with your dad?
It's just the tip
of the iceberg.
I don't want to talk about it.
Okay.
You want a drink?
Isn't it the New York
sophisticate
who's supposed to corrupt
the sweet small-town boy?
My dad's visiting my mom.
They're about to finalize
the divorce.
God, Archie, if my mom had
anything to do with that...
No. This was them.
My mom wanted
to leave Riverdale,
my dad wanted to stay.
I had to choose,
and I chose my dad.
Forget it. It's nothing
compared to what
you're going through.
He threatened me, Archie.
Said he would destroy my mom
if I didn't make a statement
on his behalf.
Said she was just as guilty
as he was.
And maybe he's lying
or maybe he isn't.
And maybe he killed
Jason Blossom, and...
Oh, sorry.
Just coming to get
ice cream, so...
Is everything okay?
Yeah, no, I'm just not in a
party mood like I usually am.
- That makes two of us.
- Whoa. Wait.
You're not actually upset that
I threw you a party, are you?
It is nice, Betty.
I appreciate it.
It's just I would be happier
if it was just the four of us
in a booth at Pop's.
Yeah. But we always do that.
I wanted to do
something special.
"The road to hell is paved
with good intentions."
Why is everything
so doom and gloom
with you, Jug?
Why can't it just
be normal for once?
I'm not normal,
I'm not wired to be normal.
How many more people
did you invite to this thing?
No one. Inner-circle only.
Did you really think
you could have a party
without inviting moi?
Or me?
Archie,
where do you want the kegs?
Screw it! One in the kitchen,
one in the backyard.
Why are they doing this?
They're agents of chaos,
Kevin.
They don't need a reason.
But if I had to guess?
Payback.
Dude, Valerie just got here.
You think she wants me back?
Archie, as my blood-brother,
it was your sole
responsibility
to ensure that something
like this never happened
on my birthday.
And now we're here.
In the middle
of a Seth Rogen movie.
This was Betty's idea, okay?
I just went along with it.
- It's so not me.
- It doesn't matter, Jughead,
you're her boyfriend now.
- What does that mean?
- It means
you're getting
your birthday party whether
you want one or not.
Dad, hey.
Happy birthday, Jughead.
How are you, Mr. Jones?
Happy to be here,
celebrating with my son.
Didn't realize you had
so many friends.
I don't.
And fair warning.
You're the only adult here.
So I gather.
- Where can I put this?
- There's a table in the den.
Dad.
- Did Betty call you?
- Yeah, she came by too.
She knows what she wants,
that one.
I'll be back.
Do you ever go down
to Sweetwater River?
- To what, fool around?
- Yeah.
- Do you?
- I've been once or twice.
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
You can cut the sexual tension
in here with a knife.
What's up, Joaquin?
Nothing.
Kevin, you know FP,
Jughead's dad?
Yeah, we've met.
You kicked me out
of the Whyte Wyrm.
Good times. Joaquin...
You wanna show me
where the can is?
- Yeah, it's right...
- Yeah, um...
I'll show you.
What is that
middle-aged Serpent
doing at a high school kegger?
Are you serious?
You don't know?
Veronica,
that's Jughead's dad.
- Really.
- Yeah.
And the plot thickens.
Betty.
- You here to roofie me again?
- No, Chuck,
I'm going to ask you to leave.
- Nicely.
- Nicely?
Because, what, you're back
to being the nice girl now?
Betty, what you
and Veronica did
when you guys got me kicked
off the football team,
you ruined any chance I had
of playing for Notre Dame.
Hell, for any good school.
I'm sorry that after you
sexually harassed those girls,
that there were
actual consequences, Chuck.
That night,
I saw the real you.
The dark you.
The Betty
that I actually think about
every night
when I'm laying in bed.
You're the last person
I expected to see
at my son's birthday party.
Just doing my job,
keeping my ear to the ground.
And your tongue
in the Sheriff's kid's mouth.
- Did you hear
anything interesting?
- Actually, yeah.
Hiram Lodge's
daughter is here.
She said something
about her father being
connected to Jason's murder.
That is not good.
Hiram and I had some business.
What does your boyfriend
say about that?
- His father, you mean?
- Yeah.
- I'll find out.
- Yeah. You better.
These kids are more
on the ball than the Sheriff.
Let's go.
You do know my dad
has a drinking problem, right?
Of course I do.
I didn't think people
would be drinking tonight.
I didn't plan
on Chuck and Cheryl,
and the rest of the school
crashing, okay?
This was supposed
to be just your friends.
You and Archie
are my friends, okay?
Everyone else,
including Kevin,
including Veronica,
are people that,
two months ago,
- I would've actively shunned.
- Why?
In case you haven't noticed,
I'm weird.
I'm a weirdo.
I don't fit in,
and I don't want to fit in.
Have you ever seen me
without this stupid hat on?
- That's weird.
- Why are you getting so upset?
- It's just a party, Jug.
- It's not just a party.
It's the fact that you
don't know or even care
that this is the last thing
I would want.
You did this for you.
To prove something.
- To prove what?
- You're a great girlfriend.
I don't know.
Doesn't it ever
occur to you just how
different we are?
Like on a cellular DNA
kind of level?
You're a straight-A student,
you're a cheerleader,
for God's sakes.
You're the perfect
girl next door.
I hate that word.
I'm the damaged loner outsider
from the wrong side
of the tracks.
Betty, come on.
Who are we kidding?
We're on borrowed time.
What the hell
is that supposed to mean?
Betty, I'm not one
of your projects, okay?
Like solving Jason's murder...
No. You're not a project,
you're my boyfriend.
Until you're sick
of slumming it with me,
or until Archie
changes his mind
and says he wants
to be with you?
Valerie, hey...
- I'm looking for Melody.
- No, no, no, can we talk?
I just wanted to say
what if... What if we made
a mistake?
First of all,
we didn't do anything.
I broke up with you
because I thought
you were a hot mess.
Clearly, I was right.
Wait, Valerie...
What is your problem, Archie?
You shut me out, remember?
It's too late.
Archie,
everything all right?
- Jughead. Hey.
- Hey, Ethel.
You didn't have
a piece of cake.
It's bad luck.
This whole night
is bad luck.
I'm ghosting.
I'll see you at school.
Hey. Whoa.
Where you going,
guest of honor?
Get out of my way, Chuck.
Oh, but you can't leave now.
We haven't even
played our game yet.
Listen up, party people.
Everyone has their secrets.
And we've all done
our fair share of sinning.
That's one thing my dear
brother's death has revealed.
So let's play a little game
to get those secrets
out in the open.
What the hell
is Secrets and Sins?
It's a variation
on Truth or Dare.
In which we own our truths.
By telling it like it is.
I'll start the game
with Veronica Lodge.
- Naturally.
- Let's begin
with the day you and your
mob wife of a mother
came to town
for a so-called "fresh start."
Tell us, Veronica,
what's so fresh
about defiling Archie Andrews
in a closet?
- That was your doing.
- Moving on
to dear Daddy Lodge...
Isn't it true
that your father, from prison,
illegally purchased
the drive-in land?
Which makes me wonder.
What else is he doing
from behind bars?
Well,
I can't speak for my father,
but I can think of someone
with a very dirty secret.
Specifically, Cheryl killing
her very own brother.
Everyone knows how much
I loved my brother.
Exactly.
But did you love him maybe
in ways that a sister
shouldn't love a brother?
And as you got older,
Jason started to think
it was strange, unnatural.
So he chose Polly over you.
So you shot him
between the eyes
with one of your father's
many hunting rifles.
This is riveting,
I can't breathe.
This game is sick.
- I wanna go next.
- That's the spirit, Doiley.
What secrets do you have
to reveal to us?
I saw Ms. Grundy's car
by Sweetwater River,
the day Jason went missing.
I told Betty and Jughead,
and then,
Ms. Grundy quit her job
and left Riverdale,
like, two days later.
And let's not forget
that Archie was also at the
Sweetwater that morning.
Oh, my God, color me shocked,
Archie Andrews.
Is that why you became
a mediocre musician overnight?
Because you and Ms. Foureyes
were pulling a Mary Kay
Letourneau?
Don't say anything, Archie.
Don't get in the gutter
with them.
Wait, what?
Andrews was banging a teacher?
Well, damn,
I wish I would have known.
I would've added you
and Ms. Grundy to the
board of conquests.
Classy, Chuck, as always.
Wait a second,
that also explains
why Archie can't seem to keep
a girlfriend to save his life.
He's got serious
Mommy issues.
Anything to say for yourself,
Arch?
Were you victim
or perpetrator?
Dilton Doiley plays with guns.
Big whoop, Betty.
So Doiley's a psychopath,
everyone knows that.
Well, I guess
it's my turn now.
Boy, do I have
a twisted secret to reveal.
Starring Betty Cooper.
Leave her
the hell alone, Chuck.
Shut up, Andrews.
Look, you may get a free
peepshow every night,
but you do not know her.
Hell, Betty doesn't
even know herself.
Everybody knows
why I got suspended.
But what you don't know...
She dressed up like a hooker,
in a God-awful black wig,
drugged me,
handcuffed me in the Jacuzzi,
and I almost drowned
until she got me to say
what she wanted to hear.
And then she really lost it.
She actually thought
she was Polly.
But, hey, you knew
all about this, right,
Jughead?
Enough! That's enough!
Get your hands
off me, snake.
Get out!
Go on!
What are you looking at?
The party's done.
It's over! Go home!
Whoa, where the hell
are you going?
What, you want to give me
some advice on my right hook?
I want you to go back inside
and talk to your girl.
I don't think
it's gonna work out.
Irreconcilable differences.
Don't run away from it.
Don't run away.
You've got something
good here.
With her, with your friends.
Something that...
Something that we could
never give you.
Also, man up.
After what I just saw
in there, she needs you.
FP.
As block captain
of the Neighborhood Watch,
I am obligated to ask you
what you're doing
on this side of town.
Don't act so high
and mighty, Alice.
You may not live
on the Southside anymore,
you may not dress like
you're from the Southside,
but we both know the truth.
Snakes don't shed
their skin so easily.
Good night, FP.
Now get the hell
out of my neighborhood.
You're still hot, Alice.
Too bad you're a stick
in the mud.
And all this time,
I thought you were a lover,
not a fighter.
I'm both.
I've got layers.
You were doing something nice,
it's just that sometimes,
when people do
nice things for me,
I short circuit.
Maybe I'm not used to it.
Maybe I'm scared.
Of getting hurt.
Or being rejected
for being myself.
I should have told you
about Chuck.
But I lied.
And instead I threw you
this party that you
didn't even want.
Why did you?
Something is very,
very wrong with me.
Like there's
this darkness in me
that's overwhelming
sometimes,
and I don't know
where it comes from.
But I think that's what makes
me do these crazy things.
Like...
How am I ever
gonna look anyone
in the eye ever again?
By Monday,
this will all be but a dream.
Trust me.
No one will remember anything.
Except maybe that I accused
Cheryl of twincest.
I drunk-dialed my dad, Ronnie.
Archie.
What did you say?
I told him not to sign
the divorce papers.
I don't even know why,
it's not like I even want them
to get back together.
Veronica,
why do I keep doing this?
I keep wrecking things.
Welcome to my life.
Every day, I feel
like there's a new secret,
a new lie
about my parents
and what they've done.
I don't want
my mom to be guilty, Archie.
I really want that
to be a lie.
Do you ever wonder...
What if you had
done things differently,
what if you had made
different choices?
What do you mean,
Every day I wonder,
what if I had left Riverdale
with my mom?
Would things be...
Would I be better off?
I can't answer that, Archie,
but we wouldn't have met,
and that would've been
a tragedy of epic proportions.
I'm messed up, Veronica...
We all are, Archie.
And, honestly,
you less than most.
Veronica. Hey, good morning.
Morning, Jughead.
Um...
So listen...
Don't... Don't worry,
my lips are sealed.
Okay. Cool.
Smithers, you've known
my parents a very long time,
haven't you?
Oh, my, yes, ages.
And would you describe
my father as a good man?
I'd rather not say, miss.
And my mother, is she...
Unequivocally good.
No doubt in my mind
about that.
Thank you, Smithers.
- Veronica.
- I'm sorry I'm late.
And thank you, Mom,
for not getting mad
that I slept over at Betty's.
Thank you for coming.
I believe in you, Mom.
And I'm ready to go on record
about how much
my mom and dad love me.
Long night's journey into day?
I can't face the music
right now.
Yeah, I understand.
So, you and Veronica...
Yeah...
- Jug...
- Don't worry.
I'm never telling anyone
anything literally ever.
Okay, good.
Thanks. That's great.
I brewed some High Point
and brought you some aspirin
for the headache
I'm sure you have.
Thanks, Mom.
So I saw that you
invited Jughead's dad
to your little
soiree last night.
I did.
I thought it would be nice.
And he was talking
to a long-haired delinquent
wearing a leather jacket.
- You mean Joaquin?
- Is that his name?
They know each other
through the Serpents.
He's kind of dating Kevin.
What?
A Southside Serpent
dating the Sheriff's son?
This is a small town,
but it's not that small.
Hi there.
Decaf skim latte
and a fresh scone.
The last time
you brought me baked goods
was because you kissed Archie.
Betty...
I just testified
on my father's behalf
and helped his chances
of going free.
That's good news, right?
My dad hired Jughead's dad
to trash the drive-in.
And given recent events,
it's not inconceivable
that he might've hired him
to do other jobs.
Like go after Jason
as payback for what
the Blossoms did to him.
I want to help
with your investigation.
I want the truth.
Whatever it is.
Whether you believe
in order or chaos,
in the end, it's the same...
We are either
in control of our lives,
or merely think we are.
Miss Veronica.
Package arrived for you.
Archie.
We're home.
Mom?
Hi, honey.