Previously on Riverdale...
You know that SoDale contract?
It was awarded
to Andrews Construction.
Mr. Andrews still doesn't know
that Daddy is the buyer?
I asked around
about those bruisers
going after your crew.
Pretty sure we both know
who has business in Montreal.
Hiram, why would he even...
Maybe he got a whiff
of your little romance
with Freddy Andrews?
When my father got arrested,
I made a pact to become
a better person.
You're the bravest
of them all, Ethel Muggs.
You hate the Blossoms
and now Polly is pregnant
with his baby.
Polly is moving home.
I will not be party
to raising a child
that has Blossom blood.
Thicker than blood.
More precious than oil.
Riverdale's big business
is maple syrup.
Since the town's founding,
one family has controlled
its lucrative syrup trade,
the Blossoms.
They were a part of the fabric
of our daily lives...
Rich or poor, old or young,
we consumed Blossom syrup
by the bucket.
That sickly, sweet smell
was inescapable.
The death of Jason Blossom
precipitated a crisis.
With the heir apparent gone,
who would inherit
the family business one day?
Certainly not Cheryl.
It was a question that brought
the wolves to Riverdale.
And now, the Blossoms
were circling the wagons
against possible attack,
from within their own ranks.
Polly won't answer
my calls or e-mails.
I mean, I get that she doesn't
want to talk to my dad,
but what did I do wrong?
Nothing.
We'll figure it out.
Come here.
Up and at 'em,
breakfast is ready.
I'm not hungry.
Oh, enough is enough,
Elizabeth,
we have a big week
ahead of us.
The Blossoms have always been
a thorn in our side,
ever since, according
to your milquetoast father,
Great-Grandpappy Blossom
killed
Great-Grandpappy Cooper.
Well, it's about time
someone brings them to heel.
I'm writing a searing,
no-holds-barred
takedown of their clan.
And you think that's going
to bring Polly home?
Maybe, maybe not,
but it'll make me feel better.
Word has it that
the Blossom board of trustees
has descended upon Riverdale
like a cabal of vampires.
Why? Now, that's a story.
I just need to find a way in.
The lawyers
are coming over this week
to take our statements
for your dad's hearing.
We're both gonna
have to testify on
your father's behalf.
What if they ask
about what he did?
Embezzling all that money?
Am I going to have to lie?
Well...
We might have to
shade the truth a bit,
Ronnie.
Mom?
Baby, I have just made
a mess of things.
Your father found out
about Fred and me.
Someone went to him
before I got a chance
to say anything...
Oh, my God, Dad knows?
Yes, and on top of that,
the Blossoms are still
after the drive-in land,
and Fred still doesn't know
that we own it.
Maybe it's time you tell
Mr. Andrews the truth.
And risk having him
walk off the project?
We've bet everything we have
on the SoDale construction.
Mom,
this is a small, gossipy town.
You need to tell Fred
about the land
before someone else does.
Archie.
If music be the food of love,
play on, play on.
Did you know
this week's
the official start
of maple syrup season?
I... No, I didn't.
Well, it is.
And every year, we host
a tree-tapping ceremony,
a tradition that honors
the Blossom bloodline.
Our heritage.
Sounds cool.
It is. Beyond.
It's also
incredibly exclusive.
Family and inner circle only.
Wanna be my date?
The maple-tapping's something
Jason and I have done together
since we could walk.
It was our
extra-special thing.
But I...
I can't face it alone.
If you came,
as my escort,
I think
I could get through it.
Cheryl, I would love to help,
but I have a girlfriend.
Maybe invite Kevin? Or Reggie?
You don't get it, do you?
I don't want Kevin or Reggie.
I want you.
You defended me
to Sheriff Keller
when not even
my parents would.
Never mind, I'm sorry I asked.
Cheryl, hold on.
"They put me in a wooden box
as I desperately opposed.
"But all my screaming
was for naught.
"My mouth had been
sewn closed.
"Curled up in bed
was just a girl.
"Needing Daddy's arms
to hold her."
Hey, Ethel.
I just wanted to tell you
how moved I was by your poem.
It felt like you were tapping
into something pretty dark,
but also pretty real.
And I don't want
to overstep...
But is everything
all right, Ethel?
Things at home
aren't great.
My mom and dad are fighting,
but they won't tell me
about what.
It's like this really
bad thing is happening,
and there's nothing that
I can do to stop it.
Like you're trapped
in a slow-motion car crash.
Yeah, I know
the feeling.
Listen, Ethel.
It sounds like you
need some cheering up.
Which happens to be
a Veronica Lodge specialty.
So...
If you're free tomorrow,
come over for lunch
and pampering.
Kevin will be there.
Yeah, come on, it'll be fun.
Just please say yes.
All right, sure.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Great, I'll see you tomorrow.
So... What was
that about?
Ethel's poem
was a cry for help
if I ever heard one,
the likes of which
I vowed never to ignore,
not after...
Uh-oh. Do we need to sit down?
Okay, so, last year at Spence,
my best friend
Katy and I kind of
terrorized this girl, Paige.
One time, we made her
drink gutter water.
Ew! Why?
Because she was there.
Because she was a misfit
and we were class-A
brutal bitches.
Anyway, by December,
Paige couldn't take it
anymore...
Oh, my God,
did you drive her to suicide?
What? No.
But she did transfer schools.
And went into therapy.
So now?
If I can make
Ethel Muggs' life
a little better,
even for one afternoon,
I'm going to do it.
Archibald.
I was going to get
Principal Weatherbee
to summon you.
Hey, Mrs. Blossom.
Have a moment to chat?
About Cheryl.
I believe she invited you
to our tree-tapping ceremony?
Yeah.
She did, and like I told her,
I don't feel
comfortable going.
Cheryl tells me
you have a keen
interest in music.
Is that true?
Did she tell you
her Great-Uncle Harrison
sits on the board of
the Brandenburg Music Academy?
They have an excellent
summer program, I hear.
It's amazing,
crazy hard to get into.
Surely not for
a talent like you.
And especially not
if I put in a word
on your behalf.
Mrs. Blossom...
At Jason's memorial,
you brought me
his football jersey.
So sorry for your loss,
Mrs. Blossom.
I thought you might
want to have this.
That was an act of kindness
on a day of despair.
You're good and decent,
Archibald,
unlike most
people in this town.
Mrs. Blossom,
I don't know what to say.
Say you'll reconsider
escorting my daughter
to the tapping.
It's just an afternoon.
And it would mean the world
to my Cheryl.
I mean, yeah. I guess
I could talk to Valerie.
I swear, Archibald,
when the light hits you
just right...
I'll tell Cheryl
the good news.
And I'll call
Great-Uncle Harrison.
Just in time,
we're celebrating.
Archie was just telling us
how he's going to some
super-exclusive music program
this summer.
Maybe. If it happens, though,
it would be huge for me.
Do you have
to audition for it?
Well, not exactly.
Mrs. Blossom came by earlier
and said she'd put
a good word in for me.
Amazing.
Terrifying.
Uh-huh.
What's she getting out of it?
I told her I'd take Cheryl
to their family's
tree-tapping thing.
I already talked to Valerie,
and she's cool with it.
Cool with you
being a gigolo now?
I'm doing someone
a favor for my music, Jughead.
I need to make connections
outside of Riverdale.
That's the way of the world.
It's all about connections.
But Jughead's right.
These kinds of favors
always come with a price tag.
Betty, back me up here.
I think it's a great idea.
Thank you, Betty.
Yeah, and while you're there,
would you talk
to Polly for me?
I just want to make sure
she's okay.
Definitely.
Thank you.
And don't worry, Ronnie,
I can take care of myself.
Famous last words, Archiekins.
When Jason died,
I thought I'd tapped
my last tree.
Now, don't be nervous.
All you have to do
is hold the bucket steady,
I'll handle the rest.
Who are all these people?
Entre nous,
they're Daddy's
board of trustees.
They smell blood
in the water.
That's why they're here.
They're worried
Daddy's losing his grip
on the company
and they're looking for a way
to take it away from us.
They can do that?
If they all vote together,
they can.
When Jason died,
it was a PR debacle.
And now, here's Polly,
pregnant and unwed.
It's no wonder
they've descended upon us
like some biblical plague.
"Nearly 100 years ago,
Grandfather Blossom came
to this sacred maple grove.
"The annual tapping ceremony
"portends each
season's bounty."
Now, I've performed
this ceremony
many times in my life.
My son Jason,
when he came of age,
performed it as well.
In his place,
I put forth
my daughter Cheryl.
Hey.
You can do this in your sleep.
- Bravo!
- Well done!
Good shot. Nice.
Mrs. Lodge,
this Quiche Lorraine
is to die for.
Ethel,
you haven't eaten at all.
Oh. Sorry. I just...
I'm not really hungry.
Anything we can help with?
Uh, my parents...
All they do is
yell at each other.
My parents are fighting
right now, too.
It's terrible.
I think my dad had some
bad luck with our savings.
Now my mom says
we're going to have
to sell the house.
My dad is just so...
Crushed.
I wish there was something
I could do to help him.
Girl, we have a lot more
in common than I thought.
We lost our place
at the Dakota.
Look, being ruined sucks.
But you have your family
and you have us.
You've got this, Ethel Muggs.
"Muggs"?
Uh, it's Dutch.
We lost the third "G"
when my Grandpa Manfred
came over.
Archibald! Come join us
before the snow starts again.
Polly.
Betty's worried about you.
Why won't you call
or e-mail her?
She fought for you, Polly,
and now you're treating her
like she's the enemy.
Polly, come along.
Tell Betty that
she shouldn't worry, okay?
Veronica, there's something
that you need to know
about that Muggs girl.
What?
Her father, Manfred Muggs,
invested with your dad.
And it's probable
that they lost a lot
when your father
was arrested.
Maybe everything.
Mom, they're being kicked out
of their house,
their home.
Well, from what
I've been told,
the Muggs family is going
to testify
against your father.
They should.
How many, Mom?
How many families
like Ethel's?
It's the risk
of doing business
with your father.
Could Mr. Andrews lose
everything,
for doing business
with you and Dad?
I'm not sure.
My God.
I don't buy this
dog-and-pony show
for a second.
Cliff can't control
his own family,
let alone the company.
Agreed.
And if he tries
to put Cheryl forward
as a successor...
Do you remember what she did
at the funeral?
Crocodile tears.
Hey.
Archie,
you don't have to.
No, Cheryl loved Jason.
What was she meant to do
at his funeral, not cry?
And yeah, Jason
was on the football team,
but Cheryl was at
every single game, too,
doing as much to help
the Bulldogs win as he did.
Also, 4.0.
Also, she has
a 4.0 grade point average.
If there's one thing
that I've learned
being in Cheryl's class,
it's don't underestimate her
and don't bet against her.
Fred, we need to talk.
Oh, God.
Hiram and I,
we are the anonymous buyers.
You're working
for Lodge Industries.
How do you not tell me that?
You never would
have gotten involved.
You're damn straight.
Because I didn't sign up
to go into business
with a criminal
like Hiram Lodge.
I'm trying to turn
Lodge Industries legitimate.
That means partnering
with people like you,
good people.
This is why Cliff Blossom
bought out my crew?
Sent thugs
to beat up teenagers?
Clifford didn't send
those thugs.
Hiram did.
He was trying to stop us.
He found out
about you and me
from Clifford.
So you have
dragged me into a war
between Hiram and Clifford,
that's great.
I know you're angry.
And I know that I have
no right to ask this...
But please
stay on this project.
If you jump ship,
I can't start over
with someone else.
So, I do the grunt work
while your husband's
taking potshots at me
and you're playing both sides?
The whole time?
I gotta take a walk.
Archibald, do you know,
when Cheryl told me
that she wanted you
to come with us,
I was a little taken aback.
Your father and I haven't been
seeing eye-to-eye lately.
I came for Cheryl,
Mr. Blossom.
And because I'm grateful
for what Mrs. Blossom
is doing for me.
The music academy, you mean?
Yeah, that would be quite
a feather in your cap,
now, wouldn't it?
You know, we can be
extremely generous,
Archibald,
to the right people.
Now later this week,
we're hosting
a banquet for the board
at the Belmont Lodge.
It's a simple thing,
a little dinner,
chit-chat, dancing.
We would love you to attend
as Cheryl's escort.
You two make quite the pair.
Oh, I'm honored,
Mr. Blossom, really, but...
But nothing.
You have to come,
I'm wearing viridian.
He'll need a proper suit,
don't you think, Daddy?
I'll have my tailor fit you.
If that's not
a problem?
No. No, no, it's just...
I'm an Andrews, Mr. Blossom,
like you said.
My dad works construction,
a fancy banquet's
not really our thing.
That's precisely
why you should come.
People like you
are the bedrock of our town.
You're hard workers.
Plus, I need a dance partner.
We won't take no
for an answer...
Archiekins.
Who would've
predicted this?
Archie Andrews
is our fox in the henhouse.
Tell us about Polly.
How is she? Did she seem okay?
The Blossoms
are treating her great.
But, Betty, I don't think
she's coming back.
I don't think she wants to.
That doesn't make any sense.
That's not Polly.
She made her choice.
We have to learn
to live with that.
No. I know my sister.
She wouldn't do that to us.
Something else is going on.
What else
did you see, Archie?
When you were in
the sticky, red thick of it?
Anything about the board?
Cheryl said that
they're worried...
That after all the scandal
with Jason and Polly,
that they might try and steal
the company from Mr. Blossom.
Well, do you hear that, Betty?
This is our story.
A hostile takeover.
No wonder
the trustees are in town.
The Blossom empire
is crumbling.
Okay, but, Mom,
if you write a story
attacking them
while Polly's
still in Thornhill...
Enough about Polly.
I mean it.
She's the one
that betrayed us,
not the other way around.
Obviously she's jealous...
Cheryl,
can we have a word?
Scatter, my Vixens.
Yes, Betty? What is it?
Polly.
Look, I don't know what kind
of Stockholm syndrome
spell you've cast on her,
but I want
to talk to my sister.
Let's not fight.
Especially not when
we should be celebrating.
Why? What happened?
Haven't you heard?
Dr. Patel just
confirmed it
this morning.
Polly is having twins.
Bless our Blossom genes!
And she didn't call
to tell me.
Hostages aren't
normally allowed
to make outgoing calls.
Can you please just give her
a message for me?
As long
as it doesn't upset her.
Tell her she
should call our mom.
She's trying really
hard to hide it,
but I can tell she's really,
really hurt and upset.
I'll pass your
message along...
Thank you.
If I remember.
Cheryl.
That was a joke, you hobo.
Of course I'll give her
your message, Betty.
But no promises
that she'll care
or respond.
Okay, Ethel,
open your eyes.
What is happening?
I was purging my closet,
thinking how you
would look magnificent
in some of these.
Here, try this on.
This is... This is so nice.
And I love this.
It is so you, Ethel.
Ronnie, I can't take all this.
I want you to have it.
These things...
My dad gave them to me.
He always brought home gifts
whenever he
did something wrong.
As a way to
make up for it,
I guess.
Did it work?
What girl is immune
to the charms
of a Givenchy bag?
And I still wear
these pearls he gave me.
Okay, but...
You don't have to do anything.
Give me anything.
I just want to be friends.
Me, too, Ethel.
Mr. Andrews! Nice haircut.
You're looking extremely
DILF-y today.
Is Archie home?
Cheryl, yes.
Um, come on in.
The Ice Woman cometh.
Hey, Cheryl.
As a maj thank-you
for coming
to the maple banquet
with me tomorrow,
I wanted to give you this.
An '84 Les Paul.
In our signature color.
You're welcome.
Okay. That's all.
I'm going now.
My claustrophobia acts up
in small houses.
See you tomorrow.
I'd give that back
if I were you.
Dad, come on.
The Blossoms,
they're helping me
get into that
summer music program.
Like, the best in the country.
And since
when did the Blossoms
ever give a damn
about you, Archie?
Well, they think
I have potential, Dad.
He's also pimping himself
out to Cheryl.
The Blossoms tried to run
our business into the ground.
Maybe if you tried talking
to Mr. Blossom...
I tried talking to him,
Archie,
he laughed in my face.
Don't think for a second
that the Blossoms
are looking out for you.
They're using you, Archie.
They look at us like
we're dirt under their shoe.
I'm over it.
What's this?
The biggest story
we've ever broken.
A tell-all expose
on the Blossom clan
and all of their
glorious corruption.
Um, would you mind telling me
what your mother
is talking about?
It's time that
they finally answer
to everything
that they've done to us,
including taking Polly.
By the way, Polly's living
with the Blossoms now,
so congratulations,
you've finally got
what you wanted.
She's officially out
of our lives.
I'm not publishing
your personal vendetta.
Well, it's a good thing
I don't need your permission.
What did you do, Hal?
Well, you kicked me out.
So, now, I'm kicking you out.
If we expose
the Blossoms, maybe...
Just maybe, we might
have a chance in hell
to get our daughter back.
You are done here,
Alice. You're fired.
Fine, Hal.
What?
I want my daughter back,
you bastard!
Mom!
Black piping
for the velvet, of course.
I'll take measurements
for the pants.
Uh, before we do that...
Could I talk to you,
Mr. Blossom?
Things aren't going great
at my dad's company.
And I know you two have
been at odds recently.
But I was wondering,
instead of helping me
with that music school, if...
Maybe you could
help my dad.
Are you negotiating
on behalf of your father?
No, no, I'm impressed.
In fact, I'm trying to imagine
if Jason would ever have
given up something
like that for me,
and I don't believe so.
It speaks to
your character, son.
But I'll tell you what,
we've already called
the Brandenburg Music Academy.
And they're very excited
to meet you, by the way.
Let's just get through
this banquet, all right?
Sit down man-to-man
and discuss what I can do
for Fred Andrews.
Is it satisfactory?
It's more than satisfactory.
My parents
are unbelievable, Jug.
Polly is locked up
in that house
like a character
out of Jane Eyre,
and what are they doing?
Changing each other's
login accounts
and throwing bricks
through windows.
I wish I'd seen that.
Okay, I'm sorry,
that's not funny.
It's like, you know
how, in a time of crisis,
people either come together
or fall apart?
It feels like
we're falling apart.
And the way things
are going, pretty soon,
the Coopers, we're not gonna
exist anymore.
And there's nothing
I can do to stop that.
Betty, don't do that.
Don't give up.
Your family is definitely
splintering right now,
but it won't fall apart,
because of you.
Because you're holding
them together.
You're so much stronger
than all of the white noise.
You're stronger
than your mother,
you're stronger
than your father.
You're holding
this family together.
So don't.
Don't let go.
I won't.
Valerie, hi.
I thought you should know,
Cheryl poured some
insane poison into my ear
about how close
you two are getting.
She legit thinks she's
going to steal you away
from me or something.
No, she doesn't.
Yes, she does.
And I don't blame her.
The new guitar, the new suit?
The Blossoms
are buying you.
For one night,
if it helps my dad
and gets me into
that music program...
Wouldn't you rather earn
your place at that table?
With your music?
All the Blossoms are doing
is opening a door for me.
What would you do
if you were in my place?
If you have to ask,
then you don't
know me at all, Archie.
Oh, my God,
did you hear?
Remember when you went
swooping in to save Ethel,
'cause you thought
she might be suicidal?
Oh, no. She didn't...
No, but her dad did.
He accidentally
swallowed a whole
bottle of sleeping pills.
He's going to be okay,
but that's why Ethel's
been so sad lately.
Now, everybody knows...
We were
tested this year.
As a town, as a company,
mainly as a family.
And it may not have
been Jason's hand
that staked
the maple this year,
but it was the hand of hope.
Don't think they're
being nice or genuine.
They wanted me to fail
at the tree-tapping.
But you're going to help
with all that.
I'll do whatever I can.
Archibald, have a word?
I'll be right back.
I just wanted to
let you know
that I've decided
to help your father.
You did? You will?
Well, you've helped
our family.
Cheryl, especially.
You fit in so well.
I think you and your father
have a very bright
future with us.
Thank you, Mr. Blossom.
Oh. "Clifford", please.
And just so you know,
you don't have
to keep doing me favors.
I like Cheryl.
And I'm happy to be
here for her, as a friend.
You know, I'm going
to be honest with you.
Cheryl's a bright girl,
but the Blossom board,
they're very skeptical
of having her play
an active role
in the company.
Now, someone with your stock
and character by her side,
tempering her more
erratic behavior...
You know, it's about...
Creating a picture.
The right picture.
Having you with us,
with Cheryl,
it tells a very
appealing story.
Which is something I think
we could all use
right about now.
You'll help us, won't you?
Excuse me, Mr. Blossom,
may I have this first dance
with Archie?
I think
that's an excellent idea.
Polly, can we talk about
what's going on here?
Just keep dancing.
And smiling.
Betty keeps asking
Cheryl about me,
she needs to stop.
As long as she's worried
about you, Polly,
she'll never stop.
Yes, she will...
If I tell you
the real reason
I'm at Thornhill.
The Blossoms had something
to do with Jason's death,
I'm sure of it.
They threatened him
and I'm gonna prove it.
Is that why you
keep blowing Betty off?
It has to be believable.
And I don't want her
trying to rescue me.
Can you please
tell her that for me?
I'm so done with this!
Do not make a scene.
No, I'm done.
I'm done!
Not now.
Polly, will you excuse me?
Betty.
Veronica, hey.
Mom, these are my friends.
This is Betty
and this is Veronica.
Mrs. Muggs.
Ethel...
We heard what happened,
and we wanted to leave
these flowers with you.
That's very kind.
Thank you.
Please don't...
Don't thank me.
We're just so glad
Mr. Muggs is going to be okay.
And we'll see you
at school, Ethel?
You don't need
to do this, Vee.
Ethel?
Mrs. Muggs?
There's something
I need to tell you.
My name is Veronica Lodge.
- My father is...
- Hiram Lodge.
Hmm.
And you're showing
your face here?
Mom, she's my friend.
She's not your friend, honey.
Her father is a criminal.
He's the reason Dad
did this to himself.
Ronnie?
Is that true?
Yes.
And I am so sorry.
I wish I could do something.
"Sorry" isn't good enough.
You want to do something?
Tell the truth.
Your father is ruining lives.
He deserves to sit
behind bars for the rest
of his miserable life.
Come on.
Cheryl.
You okay?
What did my dad
say to you?
That everyone thinks
I'm a train wreck?
Jason was the golden boy,
but me...
People hate me, Archie.
And at school,
that's fine, whatever.
But this is my family.
Forget them, Cheryl.
Forget what they think.
I think you're awesome.
Oh, Archie,
sometimes I think you may
be the only decent person
left in Riverdale.
The only person
who doesn't want
something from me.
Or who doesn't want me
to apologize for who I am...
And what I want.
What are you doing?
My lipstick's maple red,
by the way.
In case you're wondering
why it tastes so sweet.
They seem satisfied,
but Uncle Bedford keeps asking
about the drive-in land.
I am so close
to getting that land back.
Hermione Lodge will crumble.
Who would
have thought she'd
prove so resourceful?
Maybe you should've sent her
to jail instead of Hiram.
Hey.
How was your night?
I just got back
from the hospital
where Ethel's dad is.
Because he tried
to kill himself...
Because of what Daddy did...
And, for all I know,
continues to do.
I am done
lying for Dad.
Archie!
I thought it was Cinderella
that ran away from the ball,
not Prince Charming.
Cheryl, I can't do this
right now. I'm leaving.
Archie Andrews,
if you leave, the radiant sun
that is the Blossom family
stops shining on you.
And everything
we've given you,
including Brandenburg,
disappears.
Are you sure
you want to
give that up?
Are you sure you want to
do that to your dad?
Cheryl, I came here as a favor
to your mom, to help you.
Oh, Archie,
don't start lying now.
You may not
want anything from me,
but you do
from my mom and dad,
that's why you're here.
Which means,
as much as I want
you to be better
than everyone else...
You're not.
You're just like the others.
I'm sorry, Cheryl...
But I can't do this anymore.
Goodbye.
Mom?
Archie just called.
He talked to Polly.
She's safe.
She's okay, Mom.
She didn't choose
the Blossoms over us,
she's actually there
to spy on them.
You know, when I
went after this story...
I thought, in the back
of my mind that,
"What if this is it?
"What if this is
finally the time
"that she doesn't come back?"
She will, Mom.
And right now,
she's our woman
on the inside.
We're going
to write this story.
Come write with us
at Blue and Gold.
The school newspaper?
Yeah, that's what we are.
But I'm pretty sure that
our annual operating budget
is bigger than the Register's.
Val.
Val, hey.
Look, you were right.
About being bought
and taking shortcuts.
After last night, I'm done
with the Blossoms, I am.
Good for you, Archie,
but I'm done with you.
Ever since we started dating
you've ignored me,
you've ditched me.
Val, please.
Let me make it up to you.
Sorry, Archie, but unlike you,
I won't be bought.
Just listen, Fred.
So many families
have been hurt
by the Lodges.
Now, I don't want yours
to be another one.
I've decided to sell
to Clifford...
Before it gets any worse.
No, you're not.
I'm going to stay
with the project.
That's great.
Thank you.
Don't thank me.
I'm not doing it for you.
See, from now on,
everything we do
around here
is going to be legal.
A hundred percent
above board.
Agreed. Of course.
Also, my stake is 20%.
If I'm gonna put myself
on the line,
I need some skin in the game.
That's a really big share.
I'm sick of you people
using me and my family
as pawns.
Sure.
Anything else?
Yes.
You and me...
Whatever was going
on there is over.
Now, we're just
business partners.
That's it.
Right.
Ethel,
I meant what I said.
I'm sorry, Ethel,
for everything my family
did to yours.
It's not your fault
what your dad did.
And you were there for me
when no one else was.
More than once.
Seat's not taken,
if you want it.
It seemed that,
for Veronica,
the sins of the father
would remain simply that.
While Archie Andrews
returned from the brink
with one more bit of news.
At the banquet, I heard
Mr. and Mrs. Blossom talking.
It sounded like
Clifford Blossom
was responsible
for sending
Veronica's dad to jail.
Oh, my God.
If Clifford sent
Hiram Lodge to jail,
tore apart his family,
then maybe Hiram was trying
to do the same thing to him?
Yeah, by going after
what the Blossoms value most,
their family, their legacy.
That's a motive.
Winter had come
early to Riverdale.
Brutal and unforgiving.
Did it work?
Are the vultures appeased?
We're not
out of the woods yet.
But it would be nothing
compared to the storm
that was gathering.
A storm of chaos named...
...Cheryl Blossom.
Yes?
Good night, Cheryl.
Good night, Pollykins.