Previously on Riverdale...
The story is about a town,
once wholesome and innocent,
now forever changed
by the mysterious death
of Jason Blossom
on the 4th of July.
The bookkeeping position
at my company...
It's still open.
- If you're interested...
- Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, Hiram.
A donation to your
re-election campaign.
And Lodge Industries gets
one of the most prime
pieces of real estate
in Riverdale.
What did Jason do
that was so bad?
Jason and Polly had a fight.
Afterwards, Polly was
pretty devastated,
so we sent her to a hospital.
If your parents lied
about Jason and Polly,
there's probably more
that they lied about.
Dad, Jason and Polly
were engaged.
Did you know that?
I'd die before I let them
steal my daughter.
- Where is she?
- She is sick!
Fear.
It's the most basic,
the most human emotion.
As kids, we're afraid
of everything.
- The dark...
- Will you stay in my room
tonight, Polly? Please?
The boogeyman under the bed...
Mom won't let me, Betty.
But I'll turn
the night-light on, okay?
And we pray for morning.
For the monsters to go away.
Though they never do.
Not really.
Just ask Jason Blossom.
Oh, Mom, I forgot to mention.
I invited Jughead
over for breakfast.
Hmm.
So, Jughead...
I suppose we have you
to thank for Betty's
ongoing obsession
with this Jason Blossom
ghoulishness?
Actually, Mom, I was the one
who asked Jughead
to help me write it
for the Blue and Gold.
Relax, Betty.
I'm just making conversation.
Do you guys have a bathroom
I could use?
- Sure, I'll show you.
- No, no. I'll show him.
Follow me...
Jughead.
Another fun fact about fear.
Sometimes it grows up
with you.
Or it curls up inside of you,
tightens around your guts.
Archie Andrews?
Each fall,
Riverdale High hosts
a Variety Show.
But this event
is no mere student frolic.
And what will you be
auditioning with?
Uh, an original song
that I wrote called I'll Try.
Try harder!
Maybe try not sucking so much.
Take your time, Archie.
Though we do have
people waiting.
Oh, my God, what's happening?
He's choking.
Archie? Clock's ticking.
Excuse me. Sorry, I gotta go.
When I was up there,
looking out...
I don't know, I just I froze.
That was stage fright, Archie.
Yeah, but when
I'm on the football field,
the stands can be packed.
- Packed, and it doesn't affect
my game at all.
- Singing makes you vulnerable
in a way
that football doesn't.
Or maybe what I was missing
out there onstage was my team.
Or at least a partner.
What if we sang I Got You?
Archie, I'm a Pussycat.
We're headlining
the Variety Show.
What if you sang with them
first and then me?
Just this once?
- To help me get my sea legs.
- Have you met Josie?
I can't step out on the Cats.
"The Sisters
of Quiet Mercy."
What is that? Like a church?
Or a charity?
No. It's a...
"Home for troubled youths.
"Where disenfranchised teens
will learn such virtues
as discipline and respect,
"enjoying lives
of quiet reflection
and servitude."
Poor Polly.
It's been months.
There's gotta be a reason
my mom and dad don't want
me to see Polly.
But I don't care anymore.
What are you guys
talking about?
Anything I can help with?
What we're attempting
is a stealth operation,
Archie.
If we go in there
with the entire Scooby Gang,
forget it, we're compromised.
Well, don't you have to
practice for the Variety Show
anyways?
Uh, no, I don't.
Except that yes, you do.
Thanks to a certain
Veronica-ex-machina.
- Excuse me.
- What do you mean?
Oh, nothing. Just that
I had a few words
with our director/host,
and reminded him
that he's heard you sing
on numerous occasions.
Even though it compromises
my artistic integrity.
Cutting to the chase,
you have a slot
if you want it.
Veronica, thank you,
but you saw what happened.
We all did.
Playing my songs
in front of you guys
is one thing,
but getting back up
on that stage by myself...
I'm not sure if I'm ready
for that.
If it's a partner
you're looking for,
Veronica Lodge
is more than willing and able.
Veronica, I didn't know
you could sing.
Like a nightingale.
What do you say, Archiekins?
Be the Jay to my Bey?
♪ Oh, when the sun goes down
we light up this town
♪ Let your voice get loud ♪
Hold up, hold up. Look, Val.
You don't sing on the bridge.
Actually, the bridge
is meant to be sung
by two voices.
What is up with you today, J?
What is up with you
today, Mel?
You're asleep
at the snare drum...
Relax.
Josie, it's a Variety Show
in the auditorium,
not show time at the Apollo.
Whether you are performing
at Madison Square Garden
or Ace Bowling Alley,
you do it at 150%.
I'm sorry.
Did you want to say something
to me, Valerie?
It's just that I don't have
to deal with this diva crap
when I'm working with Archie.
Working with Archie how?
Co-writing songs.
- Singing with him.
- Unacceptable.
You sing with the Pussycats.
Or with Archie.
But not both.
In that case, I quit.
Don't let the door hit you
on the way out.
How's the, uh,
first day going?
Um...
It's your books, Fred.
You only have enough
in the bank to cover
three more weeks of payroll.
I just don't want to... I...
I can't let my guys go.
Last time I fired someone,
it was not good.
I trust those guys, you know.
They trust me.
That's worth everything.
Yeah, but...
I mean...
Even putting your business
at risk?
I'm waiting to hear
on this huge bid.
It's a long shot, but...
You know that new development
where the old drive-in
used to be?
I'm thinking that
the construction
could actually put me
back in the black.
If I knew who the buyer was,
I would plead the case myself.
So, I'm gonna do
the next best thing.
Mayor McCoy is handling
all the arrangements
for the buyer.
So, I invited her to dinner.
Figure I can try to woo her
into giving me the contract.
So, I was thinking...
Maybe you could be my co-host.
Yeah. I mean, of course.
Good.
Actually, why don't we
have the dinner at my place?
It's nicer. No offense.
Hey, I just wanted to
let you know,
I, uh... I bought tickets
for all the guys at work
to come see you
in the Variety Show.
Yeah, me and Hermione...
We're gonna go together.
With each other. I...
I don't really know
how to say this,
and I don't want to
make a too big a deal of it,
but, uh...
Dad, it's okay. You're good.
Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Good. Okay.
I do like her, and I...
You know,
I think maybe I'm ready...
If this is something
that makes you happy,
then I say go for it.
You're good.
Mom's good. I'm good.
All right.
Mom,
Valerie quit the Pussycats.
- Replace her.
- Val writes our songs.
She's irreplaceable.
No, Josie.
You're irreplaceable.
Everyone else is disposable.
You know, maybe it's not
such a bad thing
to try a new voice.
- Ugh.
- A different sound.
You know how your father
feels about pop music.
- But it's not pop music
this time.
- Okay,
well, he's catching a red eye
and missing two concert dates
to see you
in this Variety Show.
I would hate for you
to let him down.
I understand, and I won't.
Good, 'cause if you do,
he will somehow blame me.
Find yourself a new Cat.
Someone skinny and beautiful.
But not more skinny
and beautiful than you.
And a woman of color, please.
- Josie, don't forget
our branding.
- Yeah, okay. Mmm.
And Josie...
Don't disappoint.
Are you gonna leave Dad
when he gets out of jail?
Honey, why would you ask
such a thing?
I saw you, Mom.
With Fred Andrews
in the trailer.
Oh, Veronica.
Honey, I am so sorry
that you did.
But I want you to know
that we've... We've never
even kissed before.
Until today.
What about Dad?
What happens when he
comes home?
I'm not sure.
I'm so sorry, baby.
It just happened, Veronica.
And I know that this
must be confusing.
Yeah, it is.
So, what can I do to help?
You know what, Mom?
There's actually nothing.
♪ I've got you
♪ And you've got me
♪ And you've got me ♪
Not to be that girl, Archie,
but I didn't get the memo
we were adding another voice
to the mix.
Ronnie, hey. Great news!
Valerie quit the Pussycats.
So, that makes me what, then?
Backup?
No. I mean, you were
just doing it as a favor
to me, right?
You are unbelievable, Archie.
You literally have
zero loyalty,
you ginger Judas!
Okay. Hey, Ronnie.
What's wrong?
What's wrong, Archie,
besides the fact that you have
no integrity whatsoever,
is that your father
kissed my mother.
Um...
- Maybe I should leave.
- No, hold on. Hold on.
When my dad told me
how he felt,
it seemed like they were both
really into each other.
They're married
to other people.
Hey, my mom and dad are
separated and your dad is...
My dad is what?
He's...
He's incarcerated, right?
That is so not the point,
Archie!
Of course not. Of course not.
I'm sorry. You're right.
Do you wanna talk about it?
We can go somewhere and talk.
Or do you want your part back?
Oh, don't do me any favors,
Archie.
Veronica...
Your hunt for a new Pussycat
is over.
I can sing, and I've got
a lot of aggression
that needs channeling
into something positive.
Hey.
Don't judge
a home for troubled youths
by its facade, right?
Hi. My name is
Elizabeth Cooper.
I'm here to see
my sister, Polly.
May I see some identification?
Sign in here, please.
He'll have to wait.
Polly's room
is right this way.
Though right now
it's silent reflection time,
and she usually spends
that time in the Garden
of Deliverance.
Polly?
Betty. Oh, my God.
You found us.
You're...
Polly... You're...
With Jason's...
- Please be happy
for me, Betty.
- I am, Polly.
I'm just...
I am so sorry
I didn't come sooner.
- I should've, but Mom
and Dad... They stopped...
- No.
What did they tell you?
That I was on drugs? Alcohol?
They said you were sick.
That you tried
to hurt yourself.
And they told me you didn't
want to come and see me,
which I knew was a lie.
So, they locked you up
because you're pregnant?
It's because they couldn't
control me, Betty.
Mom and Dad hated
that Jason and I were dating.
They were thrilled
when Jason dumped me.
Jason's parents forced him
to break up with me.
Of course they didn't approve
of a Blossom boy dating
a Cooper girl.
But when I told him
about the baby,
our baby...
Oh, he was so happy,
Betty.
We were gonna run away.
Start our family
in a beautiful place.
So, on July 4th,
I woke up, I packed a bag,
and I went downstairs
to start my new life.
Just like Jason and I
had planned.
We were gonna meet
on the other side
of Sweetwater River.
But Mom and Dad found out
about everything.
When I went downstairs,
there was a woman
I didn't know
sitting at the kitchen table
drinking tea
- with two men behind her.
- Oh, my God.
They threw me
in the back of a van.
I was screaming.
I don't think I stopped
screaming until I got here,
in this place.
Have you talked to him?
Does he know that I'm here?
- Who, Polly?
- Jason.
If I give him a message,
will you make sure
it gets to him?
- Polly, Jason...
- What does he think happened?
He knows that I'm here
because of Mom and Dad, right?
Polly, you don't understand...
I can fix this, Betty.
I know I can.
You just have to help me
get out of here,
and then I'll go to meet him.
I'll go to the car
on the lost highway
off of Route 40.
"Once you pass the old
maple syrup sign,
"then you'll know
you're almost there."
See? I remember.
I'm packed. We're packed.
We'll go to the farm
just like we planned...
Polly, stop.
What's the matter, Betty?
What? What is it?
Jason...
What?
Did something happen to him?
Something bad?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
I knew it.
He's... He's...
- He's...
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Polly.
Come with me, young lady.
Now.
♪ Ooh
♪ Fallin' free,
fallin' free
fallin' free ♪
Um, sorry, Duchess.
Is our practice interrupting
your texting?
I'm just...
I'm just stressed out about...
Poor little rich girl.
What do you have
to be stressed out about?
We're doing a cover
of a disco song,
and my dad is skipping
Jazz Fest to hear it...
Okay, well, I'm sorry
you have daddy issues,
but at least your father
can be in the same room
with you.
I haven't seen my dad
in three months
because he's in jail.
And my mom is...
You know what?
It doesn't matter.
You don't care,
and it's not important.
Veronica.
I'm sorry about your dad.
Thanks.
♪ I'm tryin', though
I'm turnin' the page
♪ We're animals
breakin' out of our cage
♪ There's nobody, no one
♪ Nobody who gets me
like you do ♪
Are you gonna
do that on the day?
Because if I'm gonna be
up there with you,
- we need to be
on the same page.
- Yeah, and we will be, Val.
What's goin' on with you?
You've been in a mood.
It's just...
I'm taking a risk, too.
A big one.
Do you mean
quitting the Pussycats?
I met Josie and Melody
when we were all working
at Power Records.
We used to practice
in the stock room.
I'll never forget the day
Josie came to rehearsal
with a bag of cheap cat ears
from the Halloween Store.
I found my voice with them.
Mom?
What are you doing here?
I pay the Sisters good money.
You think they don't notify me
if Polly gets a visitor?
- Mom?
- Polly...
Jason's dead?
And you didn't tell me?
And you kept me in here?
Baby, it's for your own good.
Ugh! You always say that.
And it's not true!
No! Betty!
I'm gonna get you out of here,
I swear to God.
- I love you, Polly.
- No!
So, Myles, you being
a professional jazz man,
you must be livin'
your dream, right?
Well, yes and no.
The real struggle
is always art versus commerce.
You know, I've never really
been about the big paycheck.
But if we're talking
about the future
and long-term security,
it can't always be about
following your bliss.
Personally, I'm just excited
to see my daughter perform
with the Pussycats
at the Variety Show.
- Oh, yeah.
- I beg your pardon?
When were you
gonna tell me about this?
It just happened, Dad,
and she's...
She's really, really good.
And Val quit.
Or should I say
we were Yoko Ono'd?
- Really?
- Yeah.
That's unfortunate.
She was the real deal.
Gave your act
some much-needed integrity.
Well, I figure as long as
the kids are havin' fun,
that's the point, right?
Except it's more than
just about being fun for us.
- Isn't it, Josephine?
- Josephine?
I didn't know
that was your real name.
After Josephine Baker.
You have no idea
who that is, do you?
- Fred? You wanna get started
on that presentation?
- Yeah.
Polly needed
to hear the truth.
And I did, too.
So?
Did you find
what you were looking for?
To be honest, Dad,
no, I didn't.
You hate the Blossoms.
You hated Jason,
and now Polly is pregnant
with his baby.
That gives you a motive.
"A motive"?
A motive for what?
The night of the drive-in,
did you break
into Sheriff Keller's house
and steal his case files?
- What?
- You weren't at the drive-in.
You weren't with Mom
when she put Ms. Grundy
on trial. Where were you?
Betty,
what do you think I did?
Did you kill Jason Blossom?
Him?
You think that
he killed Jason?
Your father?
- You think that he has
the stomach for that?
- Alice...
I wish he'd killed Jason.
I wish I had after what Jason
did to Polly.
I swear, Elizabeth,
you're sounding crazy
just like your sister.
- Stop staying that, Mom.
She's not crazy...
- She is, Betty.
She...
Okay, she is depressed
and delusional.
Did you actually believe
the story she told you?
About running off
to Never-Never Land
and raising a family?
That's a fantasy, Betty.
I don't believe you.
You don't
have to believe us.
We're your parents.
And with the labor force
coming from Riverdale,
Andrews Construction
would be stimulating
the local economy.
It's a win
for the entire town.
That's it in a nutshell.
Well...
After all that
salt-of-the-earth talk,
I didn't expect you to be
another dollar-chasing
gentrifier.
Myles, Fred Andrews
is a working man
who lives in the real world.
I think Fred's bid
was refreshing.
In fact, I'd like
to award him the contract.
I'd like to, Fred,
but the buyer's
already in the process
of accepting another bid.
It would take two
shareholder signatures
to stop the process.
Pop music isn't jazz.
Beyonce
is not Josephine Baker.
- It's an impossible target
to hit, and I keep trying...
- Right...
...but he just... I'm...
Anyway, what's your sob story?
Nothing so glamorous.
I caught my mom
and Fred Andrews
in an intimate moment.
Are you gonna tell your dad?
Josie, the only thing
that keeps me going right now
is the thought of how,
when he gets out of jail,
we can all be together again.
And we can go back
to the way things were.
- Mmm.
- And If I tell my dad
about my mom,
that just all goes away.
Maybe. Maybe not.
- You don't know my father...
- Yeah, but I know
dysfunctional families.
I'm not sayin'
that what your mom's
doing is right,
but maybe there's another side
to the story.
- Hmm?
- Maybe one worth hearing?
Dad, if I tank at the Variety
Show, would you...
Would I be mad?
Son, whatever happens
at that show, or any show,
whether you go
up there and kill it
or you bomb
like electric Dylan
at a folk concert...
I'm not sure who that is.
I would still love you, okay?
Support you.
I'd be proud of the fact
that you were brave enough
to go after somethin'
that you care about.
I can't wait to see your debut
as a Pussycat, Ronnie.
- Mom, I've been thinking...
- Truly.
Meanwhile, I was wondering
if you could help me
with something.
- Are those divorce papers?
- No.
Ronnie, it's a motion.
To award
the construction contract
on your father's land
to Fred Andrews.
I know you're not
his biggest fan right now,
but I was hoping
you would sign it.
Why would I need to sign it?
When your father was arrested,
we made you a legal officer
of Lodge Industries.
Surprise!
And two out of three
signatures are needed
to award the contract,
which your father
wants to give
to a less than legit outfit.
And you want my help
giving it to your boyfriend.
I was gonna apologize to you.
If I sign that, will you stop
seeing Fred Andrews?
Ronnie, I can't agree to that.
In that case, Mom,
I'm sorry, but no.
However you're rationalizing
what you're doing
with Archie's dad,
I don't want any part of it.
It's so perfect
when you play it.
We wrote a good song, Archie.
I can't wait to sing it
with you in public.
But just not tonight.
Val, you should play
with the Pussycats.
I don't want to be the guy
that broke up The Beatles.
In your heart,
you're a Pussycat.
You'll always be a Pussycat.
Maybe.
But singing backup
with no vote, no agency...
- Well, after meeting
Josie's dad...
- Myles is in town?
- Yeah.
- That's why she's been acting
like Catzilla.
I'm betting you can negotiate
new terms.
Where does that leave you?
I was born alone.
I'll die alone.
I'll sing alone.
I'll be okay.
Hey there, Juliet.
Nurse off duty?
You haven't gone full
Yellow Wallpaper on me yet,
have you?
They're crazy.
My parents are crazy.
They're parents.
They're all crazy.
No, but what if...
What if Polly is, too?
The way she was talking to me,
the way she looked at me...
And now, all I can think is,
"Maybe I'm crazy
like they are."
Hey.
We're all crazy.
We're not our parents, Betty.
We're not our families.
Also...
What?
The car.
Wow. That's what you're
thinking about in the middle
of our moment?
No! Polly talked about a car
Jason had stashed for them
down Route 40 near some sign.
If we can find it,
we can confirm Polly's story.
One way or another.
I need to know, Juggy.
Hello, Riverdale High,
and welcome to the 75th
annual Variety Show!
Why didn't you tell me
your dad was coming?
Would it have
made a difference?
Um, yes.
Josie, I'm not singing
with Archie tonight.
Sorry to hear that,
but you know I filled
your spot, Val.
Yes...
And I also know the new girl
may be pretty,
but no way does
her voice blend with yours
like mine does.
I suppose...
There's always room for one
more kitty in my litter box.
- But Josie...
- Yeah?
Every now and then,
I want to sing lead.
Co-lead.
And only on the bridge.
Fine.
I have this killer arrangement
of Ms. Donna Summer's
I Feel Love,
if you're up for that tonight.
- I so am.
- Oh, my God!
All right, girl.
Go get changed,
'cause we're gonna rock it!
Aw, come here.
♪ Ooh
♪ It's so good,
it's so good
♪ It's so good
♪ Ooh
♪ Heaven knows,
heaven knows
♪ Heaven knows
♪ Ooh
♪ I feel love,
I feel love
♪ I feel love
What are those?
Drugs, Betty.
Wait! Jughead, put it down!
This is evidence.
This is all evidence.
Crap. This whole car
is a crime scene.
Okay.
We need to get Sheriff Keller
and then we need to get Polly.
♪ I feel love ♪
That was Josie
and the Pussycats!
Long tails
and ears for hats.
- You guys killed it.
- Thanks. So will you.
I know you will, Archie.
Okay, so this is
my mea culpa moment.
I was angry at my mom
and I took it out on you.
And I shouldn't
have tried to bench you
when Valerie came back.
Truer words could not
have been spoken.
- You holding up?
- Honestly...
I'm hanging on by my whiskers.
You?
The prospect
of total humiliation
in front of this entire town
is terrifying.
Want some company out there?
More than anything.
No. I have to do this
on my own, Veronica.
Well, if you freeze out there,
Red Troubadour,
just focus on someone
that makes you feel safe.
- Here's Archie Andrews!
- Come on. Go.
Stick to football!
♪ Can you hear me?
♪ Am I drowned out
in the crowd?
♪ Are you listening?
♪ Or is everyone else too loud
for you to hear anything?
♪ Are you just gonna
walk away?
♪ 'Cause there are
so many things
♪ I can do,
but instead I'll say
♪ I'll try
♪ To let it go
- ♪ Let it roll
right off my shoulders
- Sheriff Keller.
I got your text. What is it?
- Look, it's Jason's jacket.
- Where'd you get that?
In the trunk of a car
with a bunch
of his other stuff.
Jason was running
away with Polly.
Where's the car?
♪ Back this way
♪ I'll try
♪ To let it go
♪ Let it go and never look
back this way ♪
Archie, you the man!
Archie!
- Hi, Mom. Hi, Mr. Andrews.
- Hey.
What's going on?
- Well, I was just, um,
telling your mother...
- Um...
You know
that SoDale contract?
It was awarded
to Andrews Construction.
The buyer, whoever they are,
they approved us.
Thanks to my lucky charm.
Congratulations, Mr. Andrews.
Looks like you won.
Excuse me.
Here's the thing about fear.
It's always there.
Fear of the unknown,
fear of facing it alone...
Fear that those closest to you
are the monsters.
Fear that as soon
as you slay one,
there's another monster
waiting to take its place.
Fear that there's
one more boogeyman waiting
at the end of the dark hall.
Polly?
She was out there.
Alone, bereft, unmoored...
Where was she going?
And what would she do next?