Previously on Riverdale...
You only have enough
in the bank to cover
three more weeks of payroll.
I'm waiting to hear
on this huge bid.
That new development
where the old drive-in
used to be?
I kissed Fred Andrews.
The other thing.
It involves you
forging my signature
to get Fred Andrews
that stupid contract
to build on Dad's land.
You hated Jason,
and now Polly is pregnant
with his baby.
Of course you can stay.
Anything for
Alice Cooper's daughters.
- So where are you
gonna live now?
- I'll figure it out, Dad.
He was stealing
from the company
and selling stuff on the side.
When someone is drowning,
you can try to save them,
but not if they're gonna
drag you down with them.
The Coopers.
The Stepfords of Riverdale.
High school sweethearts
who got married
and had two beautiful
daughters, Polly and Betty...
Until Jason Blossom happened.
And now, we would hear from
the person who was closest
to him those days
leading up to
his disappearance...
Polly Cooper.
How a casual conversation
turned into an epic,
forbidden romance.
How, for reasons still murky,
their respective parents
tried to tear them apart.
How their break-up
was short-lived,
because Polly soon learned
she was pregnant
with Jason's baby.
How they became
secretly engaged
with his
grandmother's blessing
and her heirloom ring,
and made plans
to run away together,
to start a new life.
And how their dreams of escape
went up in flames.
That was the last day
you saw him?
At Pop's, when
he told me the plan,
that he was gonna fake
his own death,
and then we would meet up.
But, before that could happen,
my mom and dad sent me away.
One of Jason's teammates said
that before he ran away,
Jason was dealing drugs.
Making a one-time delivery.
He needed... We needed money.
To get away and to start over.
So Riverdale's star football
player becomes a drug mule?
He went to a bar on the
other side of the tracks
and made a deal
with some biker gang.
The Serpents?
He got an address upstate,
where he was supposed
to deliver the drugs
in exchange for cash.
The drugs you found
in Jason's car...
- Yeah.
- ...that went up in flames.
Along with everything
I had left of Jason,
including the ring
his nana gave me,
which he was
keeping until...
Okay, Sheriff, I think
that's enough for tonight.
I think Polly needs her rest.
I'll be in touch, ladies.
- I'll show you out.
- Thank you.
We're gonna get you
through this, okay?
Gotta stop
blowing me up.
- You're going the wrong way.
- You're going the...
- What are you doing?
Come on.
You're the one
who keeps accidentally
killing me.
War is hell, Jug.
No, Archie,
hell is other people.
Hey, guys,
getting pretty late...
And... Whoa!
It's kinda ripe in here.
Does someone wanna
open a window?
I got it.
- You settling in, Jug?
- Oh, completely.
It's like Archie and I are
just roommates
in a college dorm.
Oh, great. What does
that make me, the RA?
No, you're the third roommate.
All right, guys.
I got a big day tomorrow.
Yeah, breaking ground
on the SoDale project, right?
Yeah. Indeed, we are.
Sorry, 'cause I know
it's kind of a sore spot
with you, Jughead,
about the drive-in.
As long as you build something
beautiful in its place.
Well, I don't know
about beautiful,
but it's gonna be big.
- Night, guys.
- Night, Dad.
♪ Talking television
at the... ♪
Polly's convinced herself
that no one wants her baby.
Besides, of course,
the child-snatching
Blossom monsters.
- No offense, Cheryl.
- None taken.
So your mom and dad want
Polly but not the baby,
and the Blossoms want
the baby and not Polly.
That's a true Gordian knot.
It's an impossible situation.
Betty, come on.
An impossible situation
is being invited
to both the Vanity Flair
Oscar party
and Elton John's Oscar party
on the same night.
Which happened to me
one year, I know.
This is merely
an annoying situation.
But luckily, I've been
percolating on an idea,
hellishly simple
in its conception.
What if my mom and I were
to host a baby shower?
Count me in.
You want Polly to feel loved
and supported, right?
Yeah, but ideally
by her own parents.
Okay, so, baby steps, girl.
Get Polly and your parents
in the same room
in a public setting
where they can't fight,
and, voila,
let the healing begin.
Am I expected to
come to this thing?
Of course!
You're Betty's
boyfriend, so...
Oh, my God, you guys, relax.
It's just a word that starts
with the letter "B."
Betty, what do you say?
Elizabeth Cooper.
Mom?
I need you and you.
Right now.
Hey, Vic, I was just getting
ready to come out and walk
you through the day.
Hate to do this to you,
Fred, but, um...
I gotta pull my crew.
Before we've even started?
What happened?
Cliff Blossom reached out.
Says he's got
a big job coming up.
Says he needs us
free and available.
Blossom's willing to guarantee
us two years' work,
starting now.
Can't ask my guys to turn
down that kind of money.
No, Vic, I can't.
Sorry, Fred.
Sheriff Keller
told us everything.
How you're hiding Polly
at the Pembrooke?
Better than
in an insane asylum.
Actually,
Mrs. Cooper, that's on me.
I was the one who suggested
that Polly stay with us.
She's trying to help.
Unlike you and Dad,
who want Polly to give
the baby up for adoption.
Betty, it's what's best
for Polly and the baby.
Mom, that's not your choice.
Your choice is whether
or not you want to be
a part of Polly's life.
Veronica and her mom
have offered to host
a baby shower.
Well, that is
hardly appropriate!
Really?
Because I think
it's an amazing idea.
You want to be
loving and supportive
like a normal grandmother?
Then, great.
Otherwise, stay away.
Don, I just need a few guys
from your crew.
A couple to
get me started.
I did check.
I'll get back to you, Don.
What was that about?
It's all good.
How was your date with Val?
It was good.
I got you some slices.
Did something happen at work?
Cliff Blossom made my crew
an offer they couldn't refuse
so they walked.
Every last one of 'em.
Screw em, then.
Anyone who'd rather work
for Clifford Blossom
than you is crazy, Dad.
Dad?
What is it?
You always make me talk
to you about my problems.
The business...
It's in trouble, Archie.
Has been for a long time.
Big jobs are just
few and far between.
That's why this SoDale thing
is so important to me.
I can't break ground
without a crew,
so every day
I'm just hemorrhaging cash.
We've got equipment
sitting there, supplies,
bills that are past due.
Dad, why didn't you tell me?
I had no idea.
It was never
supposed to get this bad.
You work your ass off
to build something,
and in one false step
you could lose everything.
No, Dad, you're not
losing anything.
We'll figure this out.
A baby shower? Are you sure
that's a good idea? You know--
- It is.
- It's a great idea.
What about Mom and Dad?
What do you want, honey?
Do you want them to come?
I do. I mean, Mom, at least.
In that case, we'll get
her there somehow.
But I do not want
to fight with her.
You won't.
The entire Cooper family will
support you on this, Polly.
I want the Blossoms there.
- Cheryl, sure, yeah,
she's on the guest list.
- Cheryl.
And Mrs. Blossom.
She just tried to declare
you an unfit mother.
Well, then this shower
is the perfect opportunity
for me to prove
to her that I'm not.
- Ronnie? A word?
- Hmm?
Sure.
Excuse us.
The Blossoms
and the Coopers in our
pre-war apartment?
It'll be a bloodbath!
They've been the Hatfields
and the McCoys
since long before Polly
was pregnant.
Plus, I'm trying
to avoid the Blossoms.
If they find out
your father is the one
who bought the drive-in,
it'll be open war.
Against us?
They're making a play
for the land,
hoping to stop construction.
Fred and I are trying
to keep it on track, but...
But Mr. Andrews still doesn't
know that Daddy is the buyer?
All of which is to say
the timing of this shower
is just...
It's not ideal.
Plus, I can't believe
Alice even wants to come,
from what you've told me.
She doesn't.
I was kind of hoping you might
talk some sense into her?
You know, like,
mother-to-mother?
Oh, yeah, no.
Please, Mom,
she really needs our help.
Fred.
You try to hire my crew on
the first day of construction?
Opportunity knocks
when it knocks.
Nothing personal.
Yeah, it never is
with you guys.
So what is it?
The development? What?
That land you're building on,
it belonged to my family.
We founded our
maple empire on it.
Now, we were in the process
of trying to reacquire it,
buy it back,
when your mysterious boss,
he, he just stole it right out
from underneath us.
And you can't go after him,
so you come after me.
The way your boss does
business deals, secret deals,
building that
SoDale monstrosity
at the speed of light
kinda makes me think that he
has a limited amount of funds.
So you're gonna
halt construction,
bleed him out.
Reacquire the land
at a more reasonable rate.
- That's a great plan.
- Thank you.
Except you're bleeding me out,
too, you pompous ass.
You're messing
with my business,
my livelihood,
my son's future.
I don't care if you're
the richest man in Riverdale.
I will come after you
with everything I've got.
Which is what, exactly?
Go park somewhere else.
How did it go with Clifford?
Good, insofar as I
didn't knock him on his ass,
which I would
really love to do.
He's in some kind of
grudge match with
the owner of this land.
Lucky us, we're caught
in the crossfire.
And this mysterious buyer...
Does Cliff know who he is?
No, he's as
in the dark as we are.
What the hell now?
What is this?
Your new crew,
reporting for duty.
I appreciate it, I do,
but isn't there
something more important
you need to be doing?
Like going to school,
playing football?
We can work after practice
and on weekends.
Until you find a new crew.
Help keep things on schedule.
Come on, Dad. I worked
for you the whole summer.
- And these guys...
- We're bruiser studs,
Mr. Andrews.
At least some of us are.
Come on.
Desperate times, Fred, huh?
All right. Here we go.
♪ Life gives me
one more chance ♪
You must be
loving this, Hermione.
Providing sanctuary
to my daughter.
Asking me here, to what?
Gloat?
Look, I asked you here
because I'm trying to help.
So what is your plan
for Polly?
What do you want?
I want my daughter back.
I want my family
back together.
Well, then,
it's time to face facts.
Hermione, Polly is a teenager.
She hasn't even
finished high school.
The father of her baby
has been murdered.
You want to play house
with her, and throw her
a baby shower, fine.
But the very next day,
all of those things
will still be true.
And she's supposed to what?
Raise a child?
Mothers do it every day.
We did it.
Come to the shower.
Be there for Polly. Help her.
Otherwise,
you're gonna regret it
for the rest of your life.
This is awesome.
Moving rocks beats working out
in our crappy weight room.
Hey, Keller!
Looking good, looking buff.
We should get you on the team.
I prefer my contact sports
one-on-one, you know, like...
Boxing.
Pretty handy with
that wheelbarrow, Archie.
You know, if the whole music
thing doesn't pan out,
you can always have
manual labor as a fallback.
Don't even joke.
I did this all summer long,
remember?
My dad loves
this kind of work.
And I love him, but...
No, I know.
Your dad's path
is not for you.
Trust me, I get it.
He works his ass off
for me, bro,
but never asks for anything.
Always has my back,
even when I mess up.
So if having his back means
I gotta haul some rocks,
then bring it on.
Agreed.
Your dad's got my back, too.
More than some people.
Exactly.
Hey, guys, you were
a life-saver today.
I appreciate it.
Hard hats go in the bin,
and there's sodas
in the fridge.
Crap! Hey, guys,
I forgot my phone.
Hey!
Hey, get away from there!
Moose, are you okay?
Stay down.
We'll get you some help.
- Who did this to you, Moose?
- No clue.
But they said,
as long as we keep working,
they're gonna keep
coming back.
What the hell happened?
Moose, over there, he caught
a couple of guys working over
my equipment with a crowbar
and then they got
the drop on him.
Who were they, vandals?
Cliff Blossom has made it
abundantly clear
he would love nothing more
than to see this whole project
go belly-up.
I doubt that Blossom's
gonna hire some thugs
to bust up your site
and beat up some teenagers.
Maybe it wasn't him.
I mean, this is
Serpent territory, right?
Maybe it was them.
Pissed that they had to leave
'cause of this project.
- Serpents?
- Yeah.
When I worked at the drive-in,
the Serpents never bugged me.
Did you see any snake tattoos,
anything on their jackets?
It happened pretty fast.
All right,
I'll talk to Blossom,
but I mean
I don't think we'll
get anywhere unless
we can ID these guys.
That is such bull.
If this was Clifford Blossom
asking for help,
you would say yes.
- Archie.
- What, Dad? It's true.
It's also not helping.
Have you heard from Mom?
Is she coming?
She's invited.
Hey, it doesn't matter.
If Mom doesn't want to come,
that's on her. It's her loss.
Betty, I've decided...
I want you to be
the baby's godmother.
Really? Me?
Oh, my God!
If anything would ever
happen to me,
the only person I'd trust to
take care of my baby is you.
Oh, my God, Pol!
It's so wrong, Val!
Things should not be this way.
It sucks, but, please, Archie,
talk to me.
I can't keep talking about it,
I have to do something.
Hopefully not something
you'll regret.
I'm sorry, Val, I have to go,
I have to try.
Poor Moose.
Is he okay?
His name is Moose. He's fine.
Dude, what the hell?
I've been texting you.
Archie, Jughead just told us
what happened yesterday.
Though I checked out
at the words
"construction" and "site."
Moose and I are going
to the Southside to find
those Serpents. You in?
Whoa! Hey, you didn't say
it was the Serpents
who beat Moose up.
'Cause we don't
know that for a fact.
Well, it's still worth a shot
if it might help my dad.
Kevin's boyfriend
can get us in.
Get you in where?
To some bar
where the Serpents hang out.
If Moose spots them,
we call Sheriff Keller
and get these goons arrested.
Archie, the Serpents
are dangerous.
They're drug-dealers.
What?
Says who?
Polly.
Remember? Trev told us
that Jason was dealing drugs?
It was for the Serpents.
You heard my Dad, Jughead.
Clifford Blossom is
trying to torpedo him.
Sheriff Keller basically blew
him off, right in front of us.
Somebody needs
to do something.
Archie, going into that bar
is a bad idea.
Jughead, are you coming
with me or not?
Thanks for having my back.
Play it cool,
just like we said.
Keep eye-contact to a minimum.
And Moose, if you see the guys
that jumped you, we leave,
and we call Kevin's dad.
Moose? Anything?
Not yet, not that I see.
We're all gonna die.
Pay up.
I'm gonna get
this back, right?
You wish, Preppy.
Is that one of them?
I can't tell.
He looks kind of familiar.
Oh, God!
Hey.
What? You got a death wish?
Archie, back off.
What the hell is this?
You like beating up teenagers?
This isn't the first time
one of you Bulldogs
has come in here,
looking to 'cause trouble.
Hey! That's enough,
Mustang. Let 'em go.
I'll take care of this.
Not you, Red, you stay.
I'm good.
What the hell are
you doing here?
Looking for the thugs that
trashed my dad's equipment.
We figured it was
the Serpents, angry for
getting kicked off their land,
but now that I know
you're a Serpent,
I'm thinking this is personal.
Going after my dad,
his company,
that is payback, right?
For when he fired you?
Man, you've got a bigger
imagination than Jughead,
and that's saying something.
This isn't a joke.
My dad could lose everything.
You think I'm responsible?
That I've been, what, waiting
all these years for a chance
to get back at your old man?
No. No, kid, life's too short.
You don't know that now,
but you will.
I called him the second
you set foot in the bar.
Get in the truck, Archie.
♪ Our house, our house
♪ Our house
♪ In the middle of our street
Hi, guys. Good to see you.
Right this way.
- Hey. Hey.
- Good to see you.
♪ Our house, it has a crowd
♪ There's always
something happening
You're sweet to be here.
I know this isn't
exactly your scene.
What? Organizing
a baby shower?
It's totally on
my bucket list.
Mom!
♪ Our house
♪ In the middle of our street
♪ Our house ♪
Polly, look, Mom's here!
I'm so glad you're here,
and you're safe.
You and the baby.
Oh, Mom.
We're here!
No big deal, it's only the
best stroller money can buy.
So expensive.
All I ask in return is
that you make me
your baby's godmother.
Kidding!
So not kidding.
Come on, Nana Rose,
let's get you a good spot
by the food.
Polly.
Let me begin with an apology.
When I first heard about
the baby, my initial instinct,
to embrace the baby
but not you was wrong.
I hope you can forgive me.
Think happy thoughts.
So what, you're a Serpent now?
Thought you left that behind.
A guy's got to make a living.
- And not many people
would hire me, after...
- Right.
It's my fault you run
with criminals
that rough up teenagers
and trash my equipment?
You really think
I'd come after you?
That I'd put you and your kid
in danger after everything
you've done for my boy?
Look, I'm
sorry for your troubles.
How bad is it?
I got no crew. I got no cash.
Never been worse.
Let me ask around.
See if any of my guys have
heard who it could be.
I'd appreciate it.
You'll pull through, Fred.
You always do.
But you might wanna keep tabs
on that boy of yours.
This necklace
reads the baby's aura.
Predicts the sex.
Nana has dementia
and gypsy blood.
- Oh!
- What?
Is my baby okay?
Babies.
It's twins.
One of each!
This is occultism
at its most ludicrous.
But I'm grateful to be here.
Oh! Thanks guys!
Okay, now Mom's.
It's my nightlight.
When I was a little kid.
How did you...
Where did you even...
I saved it. I know how much
you loved it and
how it made you feel safe.
And I wanted you to be able
to pass it down to your
own baby one day.
Alice, it's lovely.
Open ours next, dear.
You were protecting him.
That's why you didn't tell me.
Relax.
What happened?
Did you know that
Jughead's father is a Serpent?
No.
That's why he tried to stop me
from going to the bar,
so I wouldn't find out.
After everything
my dad has done for you...
Archie. I can explain, okay?
But not right now.
This is Polly's day, so you
two need to check yourselves.
I mean it.
- Archie...
- No, save it.
Come on.
That is
a family heirloom.
Great-grandfather Blossom
used to play with it.
Isn't it magnificent?
Oh, Polly, come stay with us
at Thornhill.
Cheryl's invitation
is genuine.
Thornhill's gates will
always be open to you.
The child would
want for nothing.
You would want for nothing.
Do you think that you can just
waltz in here, with a
bedbug-infested Trojan Horse,
wave a blank check around
and steal my daughter?
I didn't think you wanted her,
else why would she have
been exiled like some pariah?
To keep her away
from your family.
Oh...
And not because
you're ashamed?
Why is your own daughter
not living with you?
She's not going to
set foot in that twisted,
poisonous house of yours.
She should be so lucky.
Cheryl, that's not helping.
She'd do a lot better there
than with you.
How dare you?
Enough! Both of you!
If you believe one lie...
This is why
Jason is dead!
Because of this hate.
This pointless,
stupid fighting.
- Honey...
- No, don't touch me.
We were supposed
to be together.
And you didn't let us
have that, neither of you.
And you know
it cost Jason his life.
Polly.
Mom.
You need to talk to her.
Polly, I'm sorry.
- It's just that woman...
- Didn't send me away.
You did.
And if you hadn't, I would've
met up with Jason,
and he still might be alive.
Or you might've gotten
hurt or worse.
I was alone there.
In that place.
I never wanted you to feel
alone, or unwanted,
or unloved.
Honey, come home.
I promise you you'll never
feel that way again.
You want me to come home?
More than anything, honey.
Yeah, but what about Dad?
Your father...
Dad's just gonna
have to get over it.
Are you sure he's not just
gonna try and make another
appointment for me?
What are you talking about?
What appointment?
Before you sent me away,
Dad made an appointment
for me to see a doctor.
Said he would be more
than happy to pay for it.
That I shouldn't have
to live with my mistake.
Oh, my God...
He didn't even ask me
what I wanted.
Dad, before you say anything,
I was trying to help.
- It was reckless.
- Yeah, but it doesn't matter.
I wanna pull my
weight around here.
I wanna help you
the way you help me.
We've both done
everything we can.
I need you to know, son...
I tried, my whole life,
to build stuff.
I tried to build a family,
that didn't work out.
I'm trying to build us
a safe life for you.
And the jury's
still out on that.
I've been pouring concrete
and laying brick
since I was your age.
That's who I am.
It's all I am.
Dad, I was thinking,
what if I have a kid someday,
and what if that kid
hates music,
doesn't want anything
to do with it,
and says, instead...
"Nah, I wanna build houses
and buildings like Grandpa."
I think that would be
pretty friggin' cool, Dad.
That would be something.
This is your legacy,
which makes it mine, too.
Polly's finally asleep.
What a mess.
I should've told you about
my dad when I had the chance.
So, why didn't you?
I was ashamed.
Jughead,
if we're gonna be together,
I want to know who you are.
All of it.
Okay.
But Juggy, we should
talk to your dad.
He might know
something about Jason.
Jughead!
Dad, Betty Cooper.
Betty, this is my dad.
Hi, Mr. Jones,
nice to meet you, officially.
And you, and you. Um...
Why don't you guys sit down?
This isn't really
a social call.
No. I didn't expect
it would be after Archie
showed up at the bar.
We know the Serpents
had some kind of drug thing
going on with Jason Blossom.
What?
Where'd you hear that?
- Jason's girlfriend.
- My sister.
The kid needed some
money to get away.
A clean-cut kid like that,
no one's gonna suspect
him of running,
so we helped him,
he helped us.
Jeez, Dad.
Did you tell the cops that?
What do you think?
Well, they know now.
Polly told them.
So if they haven't been
by yet, they will be.
Did you ever talk to Jason?
Personally?
My guys gave him some product.
When it wasn't delivered,
we figured he'd took off
with our stash, until...
Until Jason's body was
found at Sweetwater River.
Anything else you wanna ask?
Did you have
anything to do with
Jason Blossom's death?
You really think
I could do that?
It's the dark ages, Dad.
I don't really know
what to think anymore.
I'm not a perfect father,
Jughead, no getting
around that,
but... I'm no killer.
- Do you believe him?
- I do.
Do you?
I believe you, Jughead.
Honey?
What did you say to Polly
when you found out that
she was pregnant?
Did you make an
appointment for her?
With a doctor?
That you offered to pay for?
Behind my back?
So that she could fix her...
Her mistake?
Alice.
Bastard!
So you did to Polly exactly
what you did to me?
See, this is why
I didn't involve you,
for this very reason.
I knew that you
would overreact.
Honey, you
weren't ready, okay?
And neither is Polly.
We were sending
her to the Sisters.
Why wasn't that enough?
Because of exactly
what is happening right now.
Our little girl's life
is being ruined
by that mistake.
By that family.
Polly is moving home, into
this house, where she belongs.
The hell she is, Alice!
'Cause I will not be party
to raising a child
that has Blossom blood.
Get out.
No.
Get out!
Get out before I do something
that we both regret.
And I think, by now, you know
what I'm capable of.
No. What would people think?
I don't...
I don't care anymore.
And I am not gonna ask again.
Get out.
I don't want you here
when Polly gets home.
I should've trusted you.
There's no excuse.
I was afraid that
the Serpents and my dad
were the ones doing
those messed up things.
I didn't wanna
believe that was true.
I mean...
He's my dad, Archie.
I get that. I do.
But, Jughead, you can talk
to me about anything.
You're like...
You're like my brother.
Nice bro-whisper, Archie.
You are my brother.
And I'm here for you
and your dad.
So what can I do?
Pray for a miracle.
The heat is on.
If the cops come around...
This is our insurance.
In case everything
goes to hell.
Here, stash it. Keep it safe.
How's it going
with the Keller kid?
It's good.
He thinks we're legit.
Right on.
We're gonna need that
inside line with the Sheriff.
What?
We got a problem?
He likes me, you know...
For real.
Ah, you're breaking my heart.
We all got a part to play.
Including me.
I've got calls into Greendale
and Centerville.
Clifford Blossom couldn't have
hired every crew in the state.
In the meantime, we'll
just be a two-person crew.
That won't be necessary.
You need a crew?
My guys are always
looking for work.
And you've never had
a better foreman than me.
I won't leave you
hanging this time.
What if there's trouble?
We can handle trouble.
We're burning daylight.
Let's get going.
I'll catch up.
We're just gonna
get the paperwork done.
I asked around about
those bruisers going
after your man's crew.
Turns out they weren't local.
Why are you telling me,
not Fred?
One of my guys says
he knows 'em from a stint
doing time up north,
in Montreal.
Pretty sure we both know
who has business in Montreal.
Hiram? But...
Why would he...
Maybe he got a whiff
of your little romance
with Freddy Andrews?
But the real question is,
who ratted you out?
Mom had no idea, Polly.
Dad never told her.
She swears it.
I just...
I can't believe
she kicked him out.
She meant what she said.
She wants you and the baby,
or babies, to feel safe.
Which means...
You can come home now.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I tried.
Polly, we're so happy
you're here.
I'm doing this for my baby.
Of course.
You made the right choice.
You'll be safe here.