ARCHIE: Previously on Riverdale...
JUGHEAD: The story is about a town,
once wholesome and innocent,
now forever changed by the
mysterious murder of Jason Blossom
on the 4th of July.
- Can we talk, Ms. Grundy?
- About what?
You're the music teacher.
Can we talk about music?
[GUNSHOT IN DISTANCE]
We heard what we heard, and
afterwards we didn't do anything!
How would we explain why we were
together at 6:00 a.m. on the 4th of July?
- HERMIONE: Hello, Fred.
- Can I get you anything?
- A job.
- I can't very well have
wife of Hiram Lodge,
on trial for fraud and embezzlement,
balancing my books.
Oh, Hiram...
Oh, my God, it's Jason. He was shot.
What were you doing down at
the river so early on July 4th?
- Working on some songs.
- SHERIFF KELLER: Were you alone?
DILTON: I saw something
at Sweetwater River.
Ms. Grundy's car.
By the river's edge.
JUGHEAD: It's been a week since the
discovery of Jason Blossom's body.
But his death is not the first,
nor would it be the last casualty
that the town of
Riverdale would suffer.
The Twilight Drive-In where I work,
my home away from home,
a piece of town history,
is closing for good,
just when we needed a place
to escape to the most.
With Sheriff Keller
knocking on every door
and neighbor suspecting neighbor,
Riverdale, every day
that passes, is becoming
more like Salem during the witch trials.
And meanwhile, the girl next door,
our friendly neighborhood
Hitchcock blonde, Betty Cooper,
was wrestling with the knowledge
that her best friend, Archie Andrews,
was caught up in a forbidden romance.
BETTY: "Dear Diary,
Sheriff Keller doesn't
know what I know,
that Riverdale High's music
teacher, Geraldine Grundy,
was at Sweetwater River the
morning Jason Blossom went missing,
and that since Archie was also there,
they could have been there together."
[CELLO PLAYING]
[SOFTLY] She is incredible.
She's the best.
I'm usually more of a
classic rock kind of guy,
but that was beautiful.
Truly.
Congratulations, Ms. Grundy.
Thank you,
both of you for coming.
No, you kidding? Archie,
he wouldn't miss it.
I had to beg him to let me come.
Great. I'll see you
at school, Ms. Grundy.
Let's go, Dad.
Well, I was thinkin' that, you know,
if you're gonna be alone tonight,
that we could take you out to dinner.
Oh. No, I...
No, I couldn't impose.
[CHUCKLES] After everything
you've done for my son, I...
You know, with his music,
it's the least I can do. I insist.
JUGHEAD: The Drive-In closing
is just one more nail in the
coffin that is Riverdale...
No, forget Riverdale,
in the coffin of the American dream.
[STAMMERING] As the
godfather of indie cinema,
Quentin Tarantino, likes to say...
Please, God,
no more Quentin Tarantino references.
What? I'm pissed.
And not just about losing my job.
The Twilight Drive-In
should mean something to us.
People should be trying to save it.
In this age of Netflix and VOD,
do people really want to
watch a movie in a car?
I mean, who even goes there?
People who want to buy crack.
And cinephiles,
and car enthusiasts.
Right, Bets?
Totally.
JUGHEAD: Anyway, it's closing
because the town owns it,
but didn't invest in it.
So when an anonymous buyer
made Mayor McCoy an offer,
she couldn't refuse...
Anonymous buyer?
What do they have to hide? No one cares.
I do!
Also, you guys should
all come to closing night.
I'm thinking
American Graffiti...
Or is that too obvious?
I vote for anything
starring Audrey Hepburn.
Or Cate Blanchett.
Or The Talented Mr. Ripley.
Betty, your choices?
Everything okay, B?
Yeah, I'm just thinking. Um...
Maybe Rebel Without a Cause?
[BOTH SNICKER]
HERMIONE: Here you go, kids.
Thanks, Mom.
If I would have known
Mama Lodge was working
as a waitress at Pop's,
I never would have given
Veronica a spot on the Vixens.
It's off-brand, and sends a
false message about acceptance.
After her TMZ-style take-down of Chuck,
all the Vixens kind
of like Veronica now.
Do they?
Be sure to put all that
cash in the register.
You are a Lodge, after all,
and Lodges are known
to have sticky fingers.
- Cheryl...
- Honey, I got this.
Cheryl, I went to
school with your mother.
She didn't know the
difference between having money
and having class, either.
[DOOR BELL CHIMING]
Now, that's an odd combo of people.
- I'll be right back.
- No, Betty.
JUGHEAD: No. Don't...
Wait, what's happening?
Hey, Betty.
Hi, Mr. Andrews,
Ms. Grundy.
Archie, can I talk to you?
Sure. I'll call you later?
BETTY: No. Actually, now.
Just school stuff. Outside?
Archie, as your best friend,
is there anything you want to tell me?
I don't think so.
[SIGHS]
Ms. Grundy was at
Sweetwater River on July 4th.
Were you with her?
Did Jughead tell you?
Jughead knows about this?
What's happening out there?
Do we know? Is it about me?
I have a strong inkling,
and no.
Also, I'd let it go.
Yes, but you're you, and I'm me.
You do you, girl, I'll be back.
What was it like before she got here?
I honestly cannot remember.
It's not what you're thinking.
So, it's platonic?
Okay, well, maybe it's a little like
- what you're thinking...
- Archie.
Are you and Ms. Grundy, like, together,
like, romantically?
Oh, my God.
You and your music teacher
are having an affair?
We are...
...together. Look, I know
that sounds bad, but...
VERONICA: Bad?
It sounds scandalous.
It sounds like jail time to me. Illegal!
- Betty, don't go there.
- Oh, I'm already there.
Ronnie, a little help here?
[STUTTERING] I mean,
technically, Betty's right.
And ethically...
Well, what is Grundy to you, anyway,
your girlfriend?
- [SIGHS]
- Your booty tutor?
I don't know, I don't
know what to call her.
You said you were at the river alone.
You lied to Sheriff Keller,
to all of us.
Why? To protect her?
She believed in me when no one else did.
Okay, we get it.
Betty, say something, please.
[CAR HONKS]
Get in the car, Betty. Now.
- What have I told you about those two?
- Can we just go?
[SIGHS]
Oh, Archiekins...
You're in it deep this time.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
Turn down the music.
[VOLUME DECREASING]
I spy with my little eye
Hermione Lodge, full of secrets.
Riddle me this, hair
models of the damned,
why is Veronica's mother
having a clandestine tete-a-tete
with a Southside Serpent
behind a dumpster at Pop's?
MAN: Yeah, so we agree.
[ROCK MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
How hard it would even be,
if I've me a little heads-up?
Look, I am, by nature,
a conscientious objector.
Not saying anything
to either you or Betty,
was the most moral,
apathetic choice I could make.
But, Jug.
She's not going to
write about me and Grundy
in the paper, is she?
Like she did with Chuck?
[SCOFFS] Dude, seriously?
[SOFTLY] Okay. Come on.
Think about what you're asking.
If there was even an iota of a chance
that something could
hurt you in any way,
Betty wouldn't do it.
- Probably.
- Oh, my God.
I'm kidding. But maybe she has a point.
What do you see happening
with Grundy, long-term?
What do you want?
[SIGHS] I want to be with her.
I don't know how, but I wanna hang on to
what we have for as long as possible.
Yup. I feel that.
Trying to hold on to something
a lot older than me, too.
Just... If Betty's
gonna do anything crazy,
can you please let me know so
I can do something to stop it?
Thank you for taking
the time, Ms. Grundy.
Like I said, the Blue and Gold
is doing a series of articles
spotlighting teachers,
and you're our first.
Let's begin.
Uh, you joined the faculty last year.
Where did you move to Riverdale from?
Um, here and there. I was
just mostly on the road.
But you've taught at other
schools, I'm assuming?
[LAUGHS] Oh, yeah. Of course.
- Yeah.
- Right.
Um...
Can I get their names?
[LAUGHS]
Seaside High,
Centreville High.
What made you leave?
They were temporary placements.
Just filling in for maternity,
sabbatical, things like that.
This is my first permanent position.
Getting back to music,
you're working with Archie Andrews
on an independent study.
Have you ever done this
sort of thing before?
- Yes. Last year.
- Oh.
With Tomoko Yoshido
and Jason Blossom.
Jason?
- Before...
- Such a tragedy.
He was an inspiration.
And pretty cute, right?
I don't think of my students that way.
- [GASPS] No, no, no, no...
- And I'm sorry,
I really should
prepare for my next class.
It's this quintessential
rite of passage,
making out with your boy
or girlfriend at the movies.
- [SIGHS]
- Why don't we go together?
I can't promise you any action,
but maybe I'll bring you good luck.
Great. Another night,
another hag.
- [LAUGHS]
- CHERYL: Speaking of hags...
Veronica,
it's so devastating to me
that your mother has to sink to such
unspeakable lows
just to keep those knockoff
Hermes bags on your arm.
What's next, selling
her hair extensions?
My mom's a waitress,
Cheryl, not Fantine.
And your faux concern reeks
of ulterior motive. What is it?
Only to remind you of
your place in this school,
nay, the town's social hierarchy.
Threatened much?
Don't worry. You may
be a stock character
from a '90s teen movie,
but I'm not.
And what does any of this have to do
with my mom being a waitress?
It's just that I saw her talking to
a Southside Serpent last night,
in the alley behind Pop's.
They were having an extremely
heated, intimate discussion.
See for yourself.
Who or what is a Southside Serpent?
They're this gang of bikers
who pretty much stays on
the south side of town.
And thank God, 'cause
they're sort of dangerous.
Drug dealers and petty thieves.
Then what was my mom
doing with one of them?
[SIGHS] Ugh.
HERMIONE: Who knew
working would be so...
Tiring.
- Mom.
- Hmm?
Cheryl showed me a picture.
You were standing behind Pop's
with a Southside Serpent.
Those guys are thugs.
What were you doing?
First off, you have
nothing to worry about.
Come here, sit.
Now, remember Veronica, I grew up here.
The Southside Serpents may be
from the wrong side of the tracks,
but I went to high
school with some of them.
I was just being polite.
Cheryl said it looked
like you were arguing.
Arguing?
[CHUCKLES] Hardly.
He made a lewd comment,
and I put him in his place.
- Mom, if you're in some kind of trouble...
- I'm not.
Mija.
And when have I ever lied to you?
MAYOR MCCOY: I'm sorry,
but the Twilight Drive-In?
It's a blight that's become a cesspool,
and a hangout for criminals...
[STUTTERING] ...and transients,
and the deal's done.
Andrews Construction is scheduled
to demolish the lot on Monday.
Mayor McCoy,
when I was a kid,
my family and I would go to
the drive-in all the time.
We couldn't afford tickets for everyone,
so my sister Jellybean and
I would hide in the trunk
until we parked. We'd sneak out.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
It's like my home.
That's a very sweet
sentiment, Mr. Jones.
But the future of Riverdale is at stake.
Ms. Grundy showed up
in Riverdale a year ago,
out of thin air.
There's no record of her before that.
Her Facebook, her Linkedln account,
they were all created one year ago.
Before that, she's a ghost.
She doesn't exist.
The only Geraldine
Grundy I could find was
a woman who died seven years ago.
How... Where did you find all this?
The deep web.
The dark internet.
Check it, it's all
online. Simple googling.
And did you cyber-stalk
Ms. Grundy before
or after you interviewed
her for a fake article?
Why are you doing this, Betty?
- I'm not in any danger.
- You don't know that.
Yeah, I do, I'm with her.
I know what we have,
and you don't.
She taught Jason Blossom.
Did you know that?
She's taught a lot of people, Betty.
What's your point?
My point is,
you don't know anything
about her, Archie.
- Doesn't that worry you?
- Betty, let this go.
- Archie, please...
- If you're really my friend,
you'll let this go.
Okay.
I'm sorry. I'm done.
I'll stop digging.
ARCHIE: I know it's not the drive-in,
but given our circumstances...
It's perfect.
Is everything okay?
We've always been so focused on me,
my music, we never get to
talk about you and your life.
- What do you wanna know?
- I dunno.
Stuff.
Anything. Have you always
wanted to be a teacher?
No. [LAUGHS]
No, I, um...
I graduated Juilliard,
and I auditioned at Carnegie Hall,
Lincoln Center, all the big symphonies,
but I didn't
make the cut. Not even close.
I had a dream.
Sometimes that's all they are.
Just dreams.
And what about us?
Is this a dream?
Would that be so bad?
If it is...
It's a nice dream.
Where does this end, Geraldine?
I have no idea.
But we're here.
And for me...
That's enough.
So much for letting this go.
Are we really breaking
into Grundy's car right now?
How do you even know how to do that?
[LAUGHS] My dad and I fix cars together.
Thank God, she drives an old...
Okay, before going any further,
if I'm committing a felony,
I need to at least ask the question.
Are you doing this because you
still have feelings for Archie, or...
No, Veronica.
We're doing this
because Grundy has Archie
under some kind of sexual spell,
and he won't listen to reason.
We're looking for anything that proves
Grundy isn't as clean as she says she is.
Bobby pin.
Okay, Ms. Gyver.
I learned that from the Nancy Drew
- detective handbook.
- Okay, go.
BETTY: [WHISPERING] Oh, my God.
VERONICA: Oh, my God.
"Jennifer Gibson"?
Who the hell is Jennifer Gibson?
That's not the only thing.
Oh, God.
Please don't tell me you're
still on this crazy witch hunt.
It's not a witch hunt,
and it's not crazy.
- We were just in Grundy's car...
- What?
- You were in her car?
- VERONICA: Yeah,
and thank God we were.
- We found a gun.
- What?
And an ID with the name Jennifer Gibson.
This is proof Ms. Grundy
is not who she says she is.
Then who is she?
Obviously some sketch-queen
named Jennifer Gibson.
Archie, what if she had something to do
with Jason's murder?
She taught him, she
made you lie about him,
we know she was at the
river, she has a gun.
So does Dilton Doiley, but you
never thought he killed Jason.
Open your eyes, Archie.
Jason was her student last year.
Everything about her is a
huge, boldfaced question mark.
Okay, whatever her name
is, she's not a killer.
You didn't ask her, did you?
About her name?
And why there's no record
of her before last year?
- [SIGHS]
- Why not?
Mayor McCoy says you won the contract
to tear down the drive-in.
I did.
Look, I'm sorry, Jughead.
I know how much you love
the Twilight, and so do I...
Mr. Andrews, just give me one week
to track down the person who
bought the land, and convince them
not to demolish a holy house of cinema.
It's a big contract for me, Jug,
and for my guys.
Whatever they build in the place of
the drive-in could mean more jobs...
Yeah, in what? Some
hypothetical future?
You put one Jones out of work,
why don't you put out another, huh?
Jug, your dad was taking materials
from one of our job sites.
I had to let him go.
Right.
You did what you had to do,
like you're doing here now.
[SCOFFS] Later.
- Jug.
- [DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR SHUTS]
You're late, Hermione.
I had to make a pit stop.
And as we discussed, Madam Mayor...
A donation to your re-election campaign.
And Lodge Industries gets
the Twilight Drive-In.
It's one of the most prime pieces
of real estate in Riverdale.
No one can know that I
helped goose this deal along.
Especially not the Blossoms.
Your secret will be safe with me,
so long as you hold up
your end of the bargain.
[DOOR OPENS AND SHUTS]
[LAUGHS] Are you just gonna stand there?
[CHUCKLES] Archie...
Talk to me. What is it?
Is your real name Jennifer Gibson?
Who are you?
And what are you really doing here?
- Archie...
- Why the new identity,
the moving place-to-place?
Tell me the truth, please.
I...
Was in a bad relationship.
A relationship... I was married
to a man who would come home
from work every night, late,
and drunk, and with a temper.
One night, I ended up
in the emergency room
with broken ribs and
a shattered collarbone.
The next morning, he barely
even remembered the fight,
and he promised
that it wouldn't happen again.
But...
It did,
again.
So...
I left.
And I
got a divorce,
changed my name...
Then I came here.
And I...
Well...
I met you.
[EXHALES]
[SOBS]
Nice murder wall, True Detective.
[KEVIN CHUCKLES]
- Here's your High Point, Dad.
- Thanks, bud.
You need somethin'?
Can I borrow the truck for the drive-in?
- You got a date?
- No, I'm going with Veronica.
Oh, okay.
I mean, is there not a
nice gay kid at your school?
Yeah. There is.
Me.
[CHUCKLES] All right.
No cruising guys tonight.
Okay? We both know what
goes on in those woods.
- Oh, my God, Dad...
- No, I'm dead serious.
All right, we've got
a murderer on the loose
and a lot of unsavory
characters in that part of town.
So, if you go, you stay in the truck.
- [WHISPERS] All right.
- Okay?
Together.
We're sorry to come unannounced, Fred.
It's been a rough
couple of months for us,
- but Alice and I...
- We think that Archie and Betty
should stop spending time together.
Their relationship isn't good,
for either of them,
and their respective
behavior reflects that.
All right. So, if
there was anything that
you could do on your end...
My son's a good kid.
I live next door, Fred.
I see him sneaking out at night,
slinking off into the
darkness at all hours.
Alice...
Are you spying on us?
Come on, Hal.
We said what we came to say,
it's on him if he ignores us.
BETTY: Oh, my God.
Intense, right?
That's why she has a fake
identity and keeps a gun.
It still doesn't make
what she did to you okay.
She didn't do anything.
Betty, you have to accept that.
And I'm all she has, right now.
You're in over your head, Arch.
You're in this relationship
with this person who is cutting you off
from everyone else in your life.
Just think about what
you're doing, Archie.
Not ont for your sake, but Ms. Grundy's.
Is this really what's best for her?
I am gonna deal with this,
but on my terms, not yours.
Good day, Ms. Hermione.
From the dry cleaners.
Ah, thank you, Smithers.
And Fred Andrews is escorting me
to the drive-in, so all
the pieces are in place.
- The drive-in with Fred Andrews?
- Yes.
An attractive woman going with
an old friend is less conspicuous
than an old crone going alone.
You're not an old crone, Ms. Hermione.
Of course not. That was a joke.
[DOOR SHUTS]
[HUMMING]
- Finally.
- What's wrong?
What's wrong is my daughter
is hiding a gun in her bedroom,
and that's just for starters.
- [WHISPERING] I can explain...
- Oh, you will.
- [GUN DROPS]
- Now, get in the car.
[MOVIE DIALOGUE PLAYING
THROUGH SPEAKERS]
[CAR DOOR OPENS AND SLAMS]
Make some room, outcasts.
I'm having deja vu.
Yeah, senior year, we're
here, watching Candyman.
- God, I hated that movie.
- [LAUGHING]
- You picked it.
- Mmm.
Did you think I'd get scared,
and jump into your arms
like a damsel in distress?
You did kiss me that night.
The briefest of flings.
- You kissed me.
- [CHUCKLES]
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
Is everything all right?
Yes.
I'm still hungry. I'm
gonna get some popcorn.
- Oh, I'll come.
- No.
It's fine. I'm gonna powder my nose.
Excuse me.
Alice!
I'm sorry to interrupt
your adultery, Fred,
but you need to come with me.
Alice, what...
It's about the kids.
KEVIN: That hair.
VERONICA: That jacket.
Jason always adored the drive-in.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[KEVIN SNICKERS]
Southside trash.
They've been doing that
since the opening credits.
Shh!
- Screw off!
- Nice haircut, you dweeb.
[ALL SHUSHING]
[SIGHS]
Hey! You know what happens to a snake
when a Louis Vuitton heel steps on it?
Shut the hell up, or you'll find out!
[ALL APPLAUDING]
I cannot believe you just
threatened a gang-banger.
I've dealt with worse
in the East Village.
I just hate when people
disrespect my cinematic experience.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
How about a refill?
Yeah, Kev, how about a refill?
Cherry cola, as always.
Can I get a refill?
And some gummy worms and a cola.
And a hot dog?
Who am I trying to impress?
We're out of dogs.
Figures.
[WRAPPERS RUSTLE]
Not so tough without your beard, huh?
[PAPER RUSTLING]
Where's the rest of it?
The rest of it?
It was my understanding that
that was the agreed-upon amount.
[TUTTING]
In that case,
maybe we need to have a
word with your husband.
Good luck with that.
As long as Hiram's in jail,
you'll be dealing with me.
Mmm-hmm.
- Is that a problem?
- Mmm.
Enjoy the movie, Hermione.
We'll be in touch.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
No drive-in for you tonight?
I got you something.
Is this to make me feel better
about my tragic past?
No.
It's a...
It's a thank-you gift for everything
you've done for me.
[SOFTLY] Archie...
[PAPERS RUSTLE]
This...
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
You cannot afford this.
I pawned one of my guitars.
Why?
You don't need to thank me.
You shouldn't...
...thank me.
Ms. Grundy,
I don't, I don't want to
end our lessons, but...
But that's what you think we should do?
Don't you?
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
So, that bow is a goodbye gift?
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
It's a see-you-around-the-halls gift.
- A don't-forget-me gift.
- [CHUCKLES]
That is hardly likely.
[ARCHIE SIGHS]
ALICE: Well, well, well.
There they are. What did I tell you?
Can someone tell me
what's going on here?
Of course. Archie,
would you like to share with us
what you and Mrs. Robinson
have been doing during
your "music lesson"?
And please don't leave out
any of the lurid details,
because Betty here keeps
a very meticulous diary,
and I'm more than happy
to fill in the details.
[MAN GRUNTING AND PANTING]
Okay, okay.
This time I really need to go.
I'm Joaquin, by the way.
Give me your phone.
This is my number.
Use it.
Kevin Keller...
[STUTTERING] As in Sheriff Keller?
Is that a problem?
Is this a problem?
I won't tell if you won't.
ALICE: I never thought that
I would live to see the day.
I thought the one thing that we
could keep our Riverdale safe from
was child predators.
Ms. Grundy's not a
predator. She's a good person
Archie, you don't have to defend me.
No, he doesn't.
Well,
they're not denying it, are they?
They're clearly guilty.
I think the next step is
we take this to Sheriff Keller,
and let the wheels of justice take over.
Dad, you can't let that happen.
- Son, it's complicated.
- She didn't force me to do anything,
I went after her.
Everything that happened,
I wanted it to happen.
There's no surprise there.
Why are you doing this, Mom?
Putting Ms. Grundy on trial?
This isn't just about her.
This is about him.
I want you see what kind of person
Archie truly is.
Wait a minute, that
is what this is about?
Your crazy grudge
against my teenage son?
I'm never going to stop being
friends with Archie, Mom.
- Ever.
- FRED: We are done here.
- Oh, we are far from being done here.
- Stop.
- FRED: Shut up.
- Stop!
ARCHIE: Please.
You're right, Mrs. Cooper.
You're right. I'm selfish,
and I'm stupid, and
I don't deserve to be
your daughter's friend.
But please, don't hurt Ms. Grundy
because you wanna hurt me.
This isn't about hurting anyone, Archie.
It's about doing what's right,
and, of course, informing our neighbors.
Alice, I swear to God...
- You swear to God...
- Publish one word about this, Mom,
and I will tell everyone that
I broke into Ms. Grundy's car.
- Betty...
- That I robbed her,
and made up the story of their affair.
It will be like, I finally...
Snapped.
- Like Polly.
- Betty...
It'll prove what everyone
already thinks about us.
"Crazy runs in that family."
Like mother, like daughter.
- You wouldn't dare.
- MS. GRUNDY: I'll quit.
I'll quit my job. Will that satisfy you?
Yeah, it will. It has to.
And I absolutely would dare, Mom.
She has to leave town.
- The hell she does.
- Son.
Why does she need to leave town?
- Because it's what's best.
- [SCOFFS]
And Alice will keep her word.
I will.
I'll pack up my things,
I'll be gone by morning.
Ms. Grundy.
How'd you like the movie?
Quite the twist ending.
KEVIN: Oh, my God.
[DOOR UNLOCKS]
- HERMIONE: Veronica.
- What the hell was that?
I saw you with that biker guy,
that Serpent.
And don't tell me you
were just being polite.
I was handling some unfinished
business for your father.
I'm gonna need more than that, Mom.
Details,
specifics.
All right, then.
Your father hired the Southside Serpents
to help decrease the value
of the drive-in's land
so he could purchase
it at a cheaper price
using an offshore LLC.
What you saw was me paying them
for a job well done.
So...
Daddy's the anonymous buyer?
And he's doing this from jail?
He has an extremely
long reach, your father.
And he's sunk every last penny
that we have into this deal.
So...
Dad really is...
Dad is a businessman.
He saw an opportunity, and he took it.
And it was happening anyway.
Old Riverdale's dying.
He's just simply helping it along.
- But it's wrong.
- Wrong?
Well, did you like living at the Dakota
with a Central Park view?
Did you like your personal
shopping account at Barneys?
How about our family
dinners at Jean Georges?
Your Hermes?
- Those were just things, Mom...
- That was our life, Ronnie,
provided to us by your father.
Understand?
[CAR DOOR SHUTS]
[FRED SIGHS]
You are not
those things you said.
You're not stupid.
This wasn't your fault.
ALICE: Betty.
Polly kept so, so many secrets from us.
I won't have any more
secrets between us.
Not anymore.
Not if I'm gonna keep you safe.
What's my name, Mom?
Say it.
- Elizabeth Cooper.
- That's right.
I am Elizabeth, I am not Polly.
Archie is not Jason.
So stop using them
as an excuse to control my life!
[SNIFFLES]
_
BETTY: "Dear Diary, love
makes you do crazy things,
and maybe some of what I
did was wrong, but maybe...
Maybe I was right
about some things, too.
Maybe Ms. Grundy was
dangerous in some way.
Tomorrow morning, when we wake up,
the world will, yet again, be changed."
_
They'll tear that booth down, too.
Raze the whole place.
Send it to the junkyard.
And us with it.
Yeah...
Maybe they'll save it.
All the pieces.
Store it in the town hall attic,
and rebuild it in a hundred years.
Wonder who the hell we were.
Hmm.
So where are you gonna live now?
I'll figure it out, Dad.
I always do.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --