ARCHIE: Previously on Riverdale...
JUGHEAD: The story is about a town,
once wholesome and innocent,
now forever changedby the
mysterious death of Jason Blossom
on the 4th of July.
The bookkeeping position at
my company... It's still open.
- If you're interested...
- Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, Hiram.
A donation to your re-election campaign.
And Lodge Industries
gets one of the most prime
pieces of real estate in Riverdale.
What did Jason do that was so bad?
Jason and Polly had a fight.
Afterwards, Polly was pretty devastated,
so we sent her to a hospital.
If your parents lied
about Jason and Polly,
there's probably more
that they lied about.
Dad, Jason and Polly were
engaged. Did you know that?
I'd die before I let
them steal my daughter.
- Where is she?
- She is sick!
JUGHEAD: Fear.
It's the most basic,
the most human emotion.
As kids, we're afraid of everything.
The dark...
Will you stay in my room
tonight, Polly? Please?
The boogeyman under the bed...
Mom won't let me, Betty.
But I'll turn the night-light on, okay?
And we pray for morning.
For the monsters to go away.
Though they never do. Not really.
Just ask Jason Blossom.
Oh, Mom, I forgot to mention.
I invited Jughead over for breakfast.
Hmm.
[Clinking on plate]
So, Jughead...
I suppose we have you to thank
for Betty's ongoing obsession
with this Jason Blossom ghoulishness?
Actually, Mom, I was
the one who asked Jughead
to help me write it for
the Blue and Gold.
[Laughs]
Relax, Betty. I'm just
making conversation.
Do you guys have a bathroom I could use?
- Sure, I'll show you.
- No, no. I'll show him.
Follow me...
Jughead.
JUGHEAD: Another fun fact about fear.
Sometimes it grows up with you.
Or it curls up inside of you,
tightens around your guts.
KEVIN: Archie Andrews?
JUGHEAD: Each fall, Riverdale
High hosts a Variety Show.
But this event is no
mere student frolic.
And what will you be auditioning with?
Uh, an original song that I
wrote called I'll Try.
- [Feedback ringing]
- REGGIE: Try harder!
Maybe try not sucking so much.
[Crowd laughing]
Take your time, Archie. Though
we do have people waiting.
Oh, my God, what's happening?
He's choking.
Archie? Clock's ticking.
- [Mic giving feedback]
- Excuse me. Sorry, I gotta go.
[Crowd laughing and applauding]
[Reggie cheering]
When I was up there, looking
out... I don't know, I just I froze.
That was stage fright, Archie.
Yeah, but when I'm on the football
field, the stands can be packed.
Packed, and it doesn't
affect my game at all.
Singing makes you vulnerable
in a way that football doesn't.
Or maybe what I was missing
out there onstage was my team.
Or at least a partner.
What if we sang I Got You?
Archie, I'm a Pussycat.
We're headlining the Variety Show.
What if you sang with them first
and then me? Just this once?
- To help me get my sea legs.
- Have you met Josie?
I can't step out on the Cats.
BETTY: "The Sisters of Quiet Mercy."
What is that? Like a
church? Or a charity?
No. It's a...
"Home for troubled youths.
Where disenfranchised teens will learn
such virtues as discipline and respect,
enjoying lives of quiet
reflection and servitude."
Poor Polly.
BETTY: It's been months.
There's gotta be a reason my mom
and dad don't want me to see Polly.
But I don't care anymore.
What are you guys talking
about? Anything I can help with?
What we're attempting is a
stealth operation, Archie.
If we go in there with
the entire Scooby Gang,
forget it, we're compromised.
Well, don't you have to practice
for the Variety Show anyways?
Uh, no, I don't.
Except that yes, you do. Thanks
to a certain Veronica-ex-machina.
- VERONICA: Excuse me.
- VALERIE: What do you mean?
Oh, nothing. Just that I had a
few words with our director/host,
and reminded him that he's heard
you sing on numerous occasions.
Even though it compromises
my artistic integrity.
Cutting to the chase, you
have a slot if you want it.
Veronica, thank you, but
you saw what happened.
We all did.
Playing my songs in front
of you guys is one thing,
but getting back up on
that stage by myself...
I'm not sure if I'm ready for that.
If it's a partner you're looking for,
Veronica Lodge is more
than willing and able.
Veronica, I didn't know you could sing.
Like a nightingale.
What do you say, Archiekins?
Be the Jay to my Bey?
[Chuckles]
[Band playing]
JOSIE AND VALERIE: ♪ Oh, when the sun
goes down we light up this town ♪
♪ Let your voice get loud ♪
Hold up, hold up. Look, Val.
You don't sing on the bridge.
Actually, the bridge is meant
to be sung by two voices.
What is up with you today, J?
What is up with you today, Mel?
You're asleep at the snare drum...
Relax.
Josie, it's a Variety
Show in the auditorium,
not show time at the Apollo.
Whether you are performing at Madison
Square Garden or Ace Bowling Alley,
you do it at 150%.
JOSIE: I'm sorry.
Did you want to say
something to me, Valerie?
It's just that I don't have to deal with
this diva crap when I'm
working with Archie.
Working with Archie how?
Co-writing songs.
- Singing with him.
- Unacceptable.
You sing with the Pussycats.
Or with Archie.
But not both.
In that case, I quit.
Don't let the door
hit you on the way out.
[Door opens, closes]
[Door opens]
How's the, uh, first day going?
Um...
It's your books, Fred.
You only have enough in the bank to
cover three more weeks of payroll.
I just don't want to...
I... I can't let my guys go.
Last time I fired
someone, it was not good.
I trust those guys,
you know. They trust me.
That's worth everything.
Yeah, but...
I mean...
Even putting your business at risk?
I'm waiting to hear on this huge bid.
It's a long shot, but...
You know that new development
where the old drive-in used to be?
I'm thinking that the construction
could actually put me back in the black.
If I knew who the buyer was,
I would plead the case myself.
So, I'm gonna do the next best thing.
Mayor McCoy is handling all
the arrangements for the buyer.
So, I invited her to dinner.
Figure I can try to woo her
into giving me the contract.
So, I was thinking... [Sighs]
Maybe you could be my co-host.
Yeah. I mean, of course.
Good.
Actually, why don't we
have the dinner at my place?
It's nicer. No offense. [Chuckles]
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
[Playing guitar]
- [Knocking on door]
- [Guitar playing stops]
FRED: Hey, I just
wanted to let you know,
I, uh... I bought tickets for all
the guys at work to come see you
in the Variety Show.
Yeah, me and Hermione...
We're gonna go together.
With each other. I...
I don't really know how to say this,
and I don't want to make a too
big a deal of it, but, uh...
Dad, it's okay. You're good.
Yeah?
- Yeah. [Chuckles]
- Good. Okay.
I do like her, and I...
You know, I think maybe I'm ready...
If this is something that makes
you happy, then I say go for it.
You're good. [Sighs]
Mom's good. I'm good.
All right.
JOSIE: Mom, Valerie quit the Pussycats.
Replace her.
Val writes our songs.
She's irreplaceable.
No, Josie. You're irreplaceable.
Everyone else is disposable.
You know, maybe it's not such
a bad thing to try a new voice.
- Ugh.
- A different sound.
You know how your father
feels about pop music.
- But it's not pop music this time.
- Okay,
well, he's catching a red eye
and missing two concert dates
to see you in this Variety Show.
I would hate for you to let him down.
I understand, and I won't.
Good, 'cause if you do,
he will somehow blame me.
Find yourself a new Cat.
Someone skinny and beautiful.
But not more skinny
and beautiful than you.
And a woman of color, please.
- Josie, don't forget our branding.
- Yeah, okay. Mmm.
And Josie...
Don't disappoint.
- [Hermione sighs]
- [Door closes]
Are you gonna leave Dad
when he gets out of jail?
Honey, why would you ask such a thing?
I saw you, Mom.
With Fred Andrews in the trailer.
Oh, Veronica.
Honey, I am so sorry that you did.
But I want you to know that we've...
We've never even kissed before.
Until today.
What about Dad?
What happens when he comes home?
I'm not sure.
I'm so sorry, baby.
It just happened, Veronica.
And I know that this must be confusing.
Yeah, it is.
So, what can I do to help?
You know what, Mom?
There's actually nothing.
- [Playing guitar]
- BOTH: ♪ I've got you ♪
♪ And you've got me ♪
♪ I've got you ♪
Not to be that girl, Archie,
but I didn't get the memo we were
adding another voice to the mix.
Ronnie, hey. Great news!
Valerie quit the Pussycats.
So, that makes me what, then? Backup?
No. I mean, you were just doing
it as a favor to me, right?
You are unbelievable, Archie.
You literally have zero
loyalty, you ginger Judas!
Okay. Hey, Ronnie. What's wrong?
What's wrong, Archie, besides the fact
that you have no integrity whatsoever,
is that your father kissed my mother.
Um...
- Maybe I should leave.
- No, hold on. Hold on.
When my dad told me how he felt,
it seemed like they were
both really into each other.
They're married to other people.
Hey, my mom and dad are
separated and your dad is...
My dad is what?
He's... He's incarcerated, right?
That is so not the point, Archie!
Of course not. Of course
not. I'm sorry. You're right.
Do you wanna talk about it?
We can go somewhere and talk.
Or do you want your part back?
Oh, don't do me any favors, Archie.
Veronica...
Your hunt for a new Pussycat is over.
I can sing, and I've
got a lot of aggression
that needs channeling
into something positive.
♪ ♪
Hey.
Don't judge a home for troubled
youths by its facade, right?
Hi. My name is Elizabeth Cooper.
I'm here to see my sister, Polly.
May I see some identification?
Sign in here, please.
He'll have to wait.
Polly's room is right this way.
Though right now it's
silent reflection time,
and she usually spends that time
in the Garden of Deliverance.
[Inaudible]
Polly?
- Betty. Oh, my God.
- [Both laughing]
- You found us.
- [Both sighs]
You're...
Polly... You're...
With Jason's...
- Please be happy for me, Betty.
- I am, Polly.
I'm just...
I am so sorry I didn't come sooner.
I should've, but Mom and Dad...
They stopped...
No. What did they tell you?
That I was on drugs? Alcohol?
They said you were sick.
That you tried to hurt yourself.
And they told me you didn't want to
come and see me, which I knew was a lie.
So, they locked you up
because you're pregnant?
It's because they
couldn't control me, Betty.
Mom and Dad hated that
Jason and I were dating.
They were thrilled when Jason dumped me.
Jason's parents forced
him to break up with me.
Of course they didn't approve of
a Blossom boy dating a Cooper girl.
But when I told him about the baby,
our baby...
Oh, he was so happy, Betty.
We were gonna run away. Start
our family in a beautiful place.
So, on July 4th,
I woke up, I packed a bag,
and I went downstairs
to start my new life.
Just like Jason and I had planned.
We were gonna meet on the
other side of Sweetwater River.
But Mom and Dad found
out about everything.
When I went downstairs, there
was a woman I didn't know
sitting at the kitchen table drinking tea
- with two men behind her.
- BETTY: Oh, my God.
POLLY: They threw me
in the back of a van.
I was screaming.
I don't think I stopped screaming
until I got here, in this place.
Have you talked to him?
Does he know that I'm here?
- Who, Polly?
- Jason.
If I give him a message, will
you make sure it gets to him?
- Polly, Jason...
- What does he think happened?
He knows that I'm here
because of Mom and Dad, right?
Polly, you don't understand...
I can fix this, Betty. I know I can.
You just have to help me get out of
here, and then I'll go to meet him.
I'll go to the car on the
lost highway off of Route 40.
"Once you pass the old maple syrup sign,
then you'll know you're almost there."
See? I remember. I'm
packed. We're packed.
We'll go to the farm
just like we planned...
Polly, stop.
What's the matter, Betty?
What? What is it?
Jason...
What? Did something happen to him?
Something bad?
Oh, my God.
[Sobbing] Oh, my God! I knew it.
He's... [Sniffling] He's...
- He's... [Sobbing]
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Polly.
NUN: Come with me, young lady.
Now.
[Band playing disco music]
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Fallin' free, fallin' free ♪
[Music stops]
Um, sorry, Duchess. Is our
practice interrupting your texting?
I'm just... I'm just
stressed out about...
Poor little rich girl. What do
you have to be stressed out about?
We're doing a cover of a disco song,
and my dad is skipping
Jazz Fest to hear it...
Okay, well, I'm sorry
you have daddy issues,
but at least your father can
be in the same room with you.
I haven't seen my dad in three
months because he's in jail.
And my mom is... [Sighs]
You know what? It doesn't matter.
You don't care, and it's not important.
[Veronica sighs]
Veronica.
I'm sorry about your dad.
Thanks.
♪ I'm tryin', though
I'm turnin' the page ♪
♪ We're animals
breakin' out of our cage ♪
BOTH: ♪ There's nobody, no one, no way ♪
♪ Who gets me like you do ♪
[Playing guitar solo]
Are you gonna do that on the day?
Because if I'm gonna
be up there with you,
- we need to be on the same page.
- Yeah, and we will be, Val.
What's goin' on with you?
You've been in a mood.
It's just... I'm taking a risk, too.
A big one.
Do you mean quitting the Pussycats?
I met Josie and Melody when we
were all working at Power Records.
We used to practice in the stock room.
I'll never forget the day
Josie came to rehearsal
with a bag of cheap cat ears
from the Halloween Store.
I found my voice with them.
[Phone beeps]
[Sighs]
[Door opens]
Mom?
What are you doing here?
I pay the Sisters good money.
You think they don't notify
me if Polly gets a visitor?
- Mom?
- Polly...
Jason's dead? And you didn't
tell me? And you kept me in here?
Baby, it's for your own good.
Ugh! You always say
that. And it's not true!
No! Betty!
I'm gonna get you out
of here, I swear to God.
- I love you, Polly.
- No!
[Inaudible]
So, Myles, you being a
professional jazz man,
you must be livin' your dream, right?
Well, yes and no.
The real struggle is
always art versus commerce.
You know, I've never really
been about the big paycheck.
But if we're talking about the
future and long-term security,
it can't always be about
following your bliss.
Personally, I'm just excited
to see my daughter perform
with the Pussycats at the Variety Show.
- Oh, yeah.
- I beg your pardon?
When were you gonna tell me about this?
It just happened, Dad, and
she's... She's really, really good.
And Val quit.
Or should I say we were Yoko Ono'd?
- MYLES: Really?
- Yeah.
That's unfortunate.
She was the real deal.
Gave your act some
much-needed integrity.
Well, I figure as long as the kids are
havin' fun, that's the point, right?
Except it's more than just
about being fun for us.
- Isn't it, Josephine?
- ARCHIE: Josephine?
- I didn't know that was your real name.
- MYLES: After Josephine Baker.
You have no idea who that is, do you?
Fred? You wanna get started
on that presentation?
Yeah.
Polly needed to hear the
truth. And I did, too.
- So?
- [Alice sighs]
Did you find what you were looking for?
To be honest, Dad, no, I didn't.
You hate the Blossoms.
You hated Jason, and now Polly
is pregnant with his baby.
That gives you a motive.
"A motive"? A motive for what?
The night of the drive-in,
did you break into Sheriff Keller's
house and steal his case files?
- What?
- You weren't at the drive-in.
You weren't with Mom when she put
Ms. Grundy on trial. Where were you?
Betty,
what do you think I did?
Did you kill Jason Blossom?
[Alice sobbing]
[Laughing]
Him?
You think that he killed
Jason? Your father?
You think that he has
the stomach for that?
Alice...
I wish he'd killed Jason.
I wish I had after
what Jason did to Polly.
I swear, Elizabeth, you're sounding
crazy just like your sister.
- Stop staying that, Mom. She's not crazy...
- She is, Betty.
- She...
- [Betty sighs]
Okay, she is depressed and delusional.
Did you actually believe
the story she told you?
About running off to Never-Never
Land and raising a family?
That's a fantasy, Betty.
- I don't believe you.
- ALICE: You don't have to believe us.
We're your parents.
[Door closes]
FRED: And with the labor force coming
from Riverdale, Andrews Construction
would be stimulating the local economy.
It's a win for the entire town.
That's it in a nutshell.
MYLES: Well...
After all that salt-of-the-earth talk,
I didn't expect you to be
another dollar-chasing gentrifier.
Myles, Fred Andrews is a working
man who lives in the real world.
I think Fred's bid was refreshing.
In fact, I'd like to
award him the contract.
I'd like to, Fred, but the
buyer's already in the process
of accepting another bid.
It would take two shareholder
signatures to stop the process.
[Sighs]
- [Pop music playing]
- Pop music isn't jazz.
Beyonce is not Josephine Baker.
It's an impossible target
to hit, and I keep trying...
- Right...
- ...but he just... I'm...
Anyway, what's your sob story?
Nothing so glamorous.
I caught my mom and Fred
Andrews in an intimate moment.
- Are you gonna tell your dad?
- [Sighs]
Josie, the only thing that
keeps me going right now
is the thought of how,
when he gets out of jail,
we can all be together again. And we
can go back to the way things were.
- Mmm.
- And If I tell my dad about my mom,
that just all goes away.
- Maybe. Maybe not.
- [Sighs]
You don't know my father...
Yeah, but I know
dysfunctional families.
[Chuckles]
I'm not sayin' that what
your mom's doing is right,
but maybe there's
another side to the story.
- Hmm?
- Maybe one worth hearing?
Dad, if I tank at the
Variety Show, would you...
Would I be mad?
Son, whatever happens
hat show, or any show,
whether you go up there and kill it
or you bomb like electric
Dylan at a folk concert...
I'm not sure who that is.
I would still love you, okay?
Support you.
I'd be proud of the fact
that you were brave enough
to go after somethin'
that you care about.
I can't wait to see your
debut as a Pussycat, Ronnie.
- Mom, I've been thinking...
- Truly.
Meanwhile, I was wondering if
you could help me with something.
- Are those divorce papers?
- No. [Chuckles]
- [Sighs]
- Ronnie, it's a motion.
To award the construction contract
on your father's land to Fred Andrews.
I know you're not his
biggest fan right now,
but I was hoping you would sign it.
Why would I need to sign it?
When your father was arrested, we made
you a legal officer of Lodge Industries.
Surprise! [Chuckles]
And two out of three signatures
are needed to award the contract,
which your father wants to give
to a less than legit outfit.
And you want my help
giving it to your boyfriend.
I was gonna apologize to you.
If I sign that, will you
stop seeing Fred Andrews?
Ronnie, I can't agree to that.
In that case, Mom, I'm sorry, but no.
However you're rationalizing what
you're doing with Archie's dad,
I don't want any part of it.
It's so perfect when you play it.
We wrote a good song, Archie.
I can't wait to sing
it with you in public.
But just not tonight.
Val, you should play with the Pussycats.
I don't want to be the guy
that broke up The Beatles.
In your heart, you're a Pussycat.
You'll always be a Pussycat.
Maybe.
But singing backup with
no vote, no agency...
- Well, after meeting Josie's dad...
- Myles is in town?
Yeah.
That's why she's been
acting like Catzilla.
I'm betting you can negotiate new terms.
Where does that leave you?
I was born alone. I'll
die alone. I'll sing alone.
I'll be okay.
[Tapping on window]
Hey there, Juliet.
Nurse off duty?
You haven't gone full Yellow
Wallpaper on me yet, have you?
[Sighs]
They're crazy.
My parents are crazy.
They're parents. They're all crazy.
No, but what if...
What if Polly is, too?
The way she was talking to
me, the way she looked at me...
And now, all I can think is,
"Maybe I'm crazy like they are."
- Hey.
- [Sighs]
We're all crazy.
[Sighs and chuckles]
We're not our parents, Betty.
We're not our families.
Also...
What?
- The car.
- [Sighs]
Wow. That's what you're thinking
about in the middle of our moment?
No! Polly talked about a car
Jason had stashed for them
down Route 40 near some sign.
If we can find it, we
can confirm Polly's story.
One way or another.
I need to know, Juggy.
Hello, Riverdale High, and welcome
to the 75th annual Variety Show!
[Crowd cheering and applauding]
Why didn't you tell
me your dad was coming?
Would it have made a difference?
- Um, yes.
- [Sighs]
Josie, I'm not singing
with Archie tonight.
[Sighs] Sorry to hear that, but
you know I filled your spot, Val.
Yes...
And I also know the
new girl may be pretty,
but no way does her voice
blend with yours like mine does.
[Sighs]
I suppose...
There's always room for one
more kitty in my litter box.
- But Josie...
- [Laughs] Yeah?
Every now and then, I want to sing lead.
Co-lead. And only on the bridge.
Fine.
I have this killer arrangement of
Ms. Donna Summer's I Feel Love,
if you're up for that tonight.
- I so am.
- Oh, my God! [Laughs]
All right, girl. Go get changed,
'cause we're gonna rock it!
Aw, come here.
[Band plauing I Felll Love]
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's so good, it's so good ♪
♪ It's so good ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Heaven knows, heaven knows ♪
♪ Heaven knows ♪
ALL: ♪ Ooh ♪
♪ I feel love, I feel love ♪
♪ I feel love ♪
[I Felll Love Continues]
- [Jughead vreathing heavily]
- What are those?
Drugs, Betty.
Wait! Jughead, put it down! This
is evidence. This is all evidence.
Crap. This whole car is a crime scene.
- [Camera shutter clicking]
- Okay.
We need to get Sheriff Keller
and then we need to get Polly.
ALL: ♪ I feel love ♪
[All singing in harmony]
[Audience cheering and applauding]
[Cheering and applauding continues]
That was Josie and the Pussycats!
Long tails and ears for hats.
- You guys killed it.
- Thanks. So will you.
I know you will, Archie.
[Sighs]
Okay, so this is my mea culpa moment.
I was angry at my mom
and I took it out on you.
And I shouldn't have tried to
bench you when Valerie came back.
Truer words could not have been spoken.
- You holding up?
- Honestly...
I'm hanging on by my whiskers. You?
The prospect of total humiliation
in front of this entire town
is terrifying.
Want some company out there?
More than anything.
No. I have to do this
on my own, Veronica.
Well, if you freeze out
there, Red Troubadour,
just focus on someone
that makes you feel safe.
- KEVIN: Here's Archie Andrews!
- Come on. Go.
[Crowd applauding]
[Crowd cheering and applauding]
- REGGIE: Stick to football!
- [Boys chucking]
[Playing I'll Try]
♪ Can you hear me? ♪
♪ Am I drowned out in the crowd?
♪ Are you listening? ♪
♪ Or is everyone else too
loud for you to hear anything? ♪
♪ Are you just gonna walk away? ♪
♪ 'Cause there are so many things ♪
♪ I can do, but instead I'll say ♪
♪ I'll try ♪
♪ To let it go ♪
Sheriff Keller.
- I got your text. What is it?
- [I'll Try Continues]
- Look, it's Jason's jacket.
- Where'd you get that?
In the trunk of a car with
a bunch of his other stuff.
Jason was running away with Polly.
- Where's the car?
- [Both sighs]
[Archie vocalizing]
♪ Back this way ♪
♪ I'll try ♪
♪ To let it go ♪
♪ Let it go and never
look back this way ♪
[Audience cheering and applauding]
BOY: Archie, you the man!
[Boys hooting]
Archie!
[Laughs]
- Hi, Mom. Hi, Mr. Andrews.
- FRED: Hey.
What's going on?
Well, I was just,
um, telling your mother...
You know that SoDale contract?
It was awarded to Andrews Construction.
The buyer, whoever they are, they
approved us. Thanks to my lucky charm.
[Both sighs]
Congratulations, Mr. Andrews.
Looks like you won.
Excuse me.
JUGHEAD: Here's the thing about fear.
It's always there.
Fear of the unknown, fear
of facing it alone...
Fear that those closest
to you are the monsters.
Fear that as soon as you slay one,
there's another monster
waiting to take its place.
[Thunder cracking]
Fear that there'sone more boogeyman
waiting at the end of the dark hall.
[Thunder cracking]
BETTY: Polly?
JUGHEAD: She was out there.
Alone, bereft, unmoored...
- Where was she going?
- [Thunder cracking]
And what would she do next?
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --