Previously on Riverdale...
The story is about a town,
once wholesome and innocent,
now forever changed
by the mysterious murder
of Jason Blossom
on the 4th of July.
- Can we talk, Ms. Grundy?
- About what?
You're the music teacher.
Can we talk about music?
We heard what we heard,
and afterwards
we didn't do anything!
How would we explain why we
were together at 6:00 a.m.
on the 4th of July?
Polly and Jason dated,
and Jason hurt Polly.
Oh, my God, Jason.
He was shot.
Jason's death is now being
treated as a homicide.
They'll find out soon enough.
That I'm guilty.
Guilt, innocence.
Good, evil.
Life, death.
As the shadows around
Riverdale deepened,
the lines that separated
these polar opposites
blurred and distorted.
"I'm guilty," Cheryl said
in Biology class.
But of what?
To clarify,
I didn't mean I was guilty
of killing Jason.
I loved him more
than I do myself.
But I am guilty
of lying about what
happened on July 4th.
The autopsy puts his
death about July 11th.
When was the last time
you saw your brother?
It was July 4th.
I don't know what happened
the week after that, but...
Cheryl, in your own words,
what happened at
Sweetwater River?
The plan was bananas,
even for me.
Jason wanted to leave
Riverdale and never come back.
He asked for my help
to stage a tragic accident,
so that our mom and dad
wouldn't come after him.
Our story would be,
we went for an early
morning boat ride,
and the boat tipped,
and capsized,
and Jason drowned.
In fact, we made
it to the other side
dry as bones.
We said goodbye
on the Greendale side
of Sweetwater River.
He promised he'd call me
as soon as he was in a place
where he couldn't be reached
or pulled back by our parents.
One month, at the most.
Every day, I waited for him
to call, for an email.
You tell anyone
about the plan?
Any way that you can
corroborate it?
And you have no idea
why your brother
wanted to run away,
fake his own death?
Doesn't that seem cruel?
No, he wasn't...
Jason wasn't cruel.
So maybe this is all
just a web of lies
you're spinning to
cover your own tracks.
I didn't kill Jason!
There was a gunshot
that morning. We heard
a gunshot on July 4th.
Maybe whoever killed Jason
took a shot at him,
and missed that morning.
You heard a gunshot,
and you're just
telling us this now?
I was upset.
My brother was murdered.
So upset that you
sang and danced at
a pep rally yesterday.
What the hell is
going on here?
Mommy.
- Don't say another
word, Cheryl.
Get up. Why didn't
you call us?
Because she's
a liar, Penelope.
When we get home,
you're telling us
everything.
Subtittle By | SupunWe |
Hot off the presses.
Mom.
First you leak
Jason Blossom's autopsy
report, and now this?
People are loving
the coverage.
You have to stop
sensationalizing
this horrible thing.
It's news, Betty.
We own the Riverdale Register.
We have a responsibility
to keep the people informed.
- Whatever Jason did to Polly,
he's still a person.
- You reap what you sow.
You should be writing
about the real story.
What happened to Jason?
Who was holding him captive?
Why was he frozen?
And who shot that gun
on July 4th?
Well, if you are
so keen on reporting,
why don't you come work
with your father and me?
The Register could really use
a Lois Lane type like you.
I think I know
something that can help with
the Blossom investigation.
People are saying
Cheryl heard a gunshot?
That's what she's
claiming, yes.
I heard it, too.
I was there that morning.
I didn't say anything because
at first, like everyone,
I thought Jason had drowned.
But then when the autopsy came
out and said he died later...
What were you doing
down at the river so early
on July 4th?
Um, working on some songs.
I, uh...
Write songs.
- Did you see
who fired the shot?
- No, sir.
Were you alone?
No, sir.
Who were you with?
Let's make it a 4th of July
you'll never forget.
My dog, Vegas.
So, are you a suspect now?
My dad says we all are,
including me.
Not me, girl.
I don't know these people.
Guys, should we maybe
re-binge Making a Murderer
on Netflix tonight?
Sorry. Can't. Gotta stay late
to work on the paper.
Count me out, too.
- I've got a date tonight.
- You do?
Which Riverdale hottie
made the cut?
Hey, Vee-Lo.
I'll swing by the Pembrooke
to pick you up at 8:00?
I'll be waiting.
Cool.
- Chuck Clayton?
- You're going on
a date with Chuck?
He's kind of a player.
Who cares?
He's the hottest of hot,
and he's the varsity
football coach's son.
In Riverdale, that's like
dating a Kennedy.
If print journalism is dead,
what am I doing here?
The Blue and Gold isn't dead,
Juggy. It's just dormant.
But waking up.
You're writing a novel, right?
About Jason Blossom's murder?
I am.
Riverdale's very own In Cold Blood.
Which started out
as a series of articles.
I'm hoping you'll come write
for the Blue and Gold.
I just don't think
the school paper's
the right fit for my voice.
Juggy...
Jason's death
changed Riverdale.
People don't want
to admit that, but it's true.
We all feel it.
Nothing this bad was ever
supposed to happen
here, but it did.
I want to know why.
Would I get complete freedom?
I'll help, and edit...
And suggest.
But it's your story,
it's your voice.
Doesn't sound like
complete freedom, but...
I'm in.
Okay great!
Um, in that case, I have
your first assignment.
There's one person who was
at the river on July 4th
that no one's talking about.
- Dilton Doiley
and his Scouts.
- Exactly.
Hey.
I texted. Where were you?
Football practice.
Then I was writing.
Songs?
Your music?
I thought you and Jughead were
on a road trip on the 4th.
Then I talked
with Sheriff Keller.
So, guess that was a lie.
- Dad, we were gonna go, but...
- You should have
come to me, Archie.
We could've gone
to the Sheriff together.
I didn't want to
drag you into it, Dad.
That was an error in judgment.
Sorry, Dad.
Sorry I'm not perfect.
You know, you're pretty far
from perfect lately, Archie.
That's why you're grounded.
What? Are you serious?
So, in this house, every
night for two weeks, 7:00.
You want some alone time
with your music? You got it.
- I'm not 10 years old, Dad!
You can't just...
- You wanna go for three?
Okay, okay, let me
try again. Let me try again.
- Let me see it.
- You don't trust me?
No, no, no, fine.
You can take it.
Okay, let me see.
Photo approval.
Fine.
You are different than what
I thought you'd be.
A former It Girl from
New York, made off
like a fall from grace?
I assumed you'd
be high maintenance.
Now tell me, what do you
miss most about home?
Only everything.
I forgot how exhausting
it is to be the new kid.
Try being the new kid whose
dad is also the new teacher.
And the new coach.
Well, from an outsider's
point of view,
you've not only
proven yourself,
but you've raised the bar
for everyone around you.
Varsity football, Dean's List.
Ivy League aspirations.
Oh, yes, you've been
vetted handsome.
Veronica Lodge is nothing
if not an informed consumer.
I'm gonna have my
hands full with you, huh?
I'm betting you can handle it.
Why did you tell them
about the gunshot?
They were gonna crucify
Cheryl. I had to help her.
You were in the clear.
We were in the clear.
I left your name out of it.
So it's not that big a deal.
No big deal, Archie?
You are caught up
in a murder investigation.
What if Sheriff Keller
decides to keep digging,
and it somehow leads to us,
- to our relationship?
- I'll stick to my story.
I'll protect you.
I'm suspending our lessons.
What?
So, how'd it go with Chuck?
Chuck has muscles for days,
but his conversation
is not the stuff
of Oscar Wilde,
or even Diablo Cody.
Hey, Veronica.
How was the Sticky Maple
you had last night?
- The what now?
- The Sticky Maple
Chuck gave you?
How was it?
We had a brownie sundae,
if that's what you
hyenas mean.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
What the hell
is a Sticky Maple?
It's kind of what
it sounds like.
It's a Riverdale thing.
No, Kevin, it's a
slut-shaming thing.
And I'm neither a slut,
nor am I going to be shamed
by someone named, excuse me,
Chuck Clayton.
Does he really think
he can get away with this?
Does he not know who I am?
I will cut the brakes on
his souped-up phallic symbol.
Or we can go to
Principal Weatherbee.
About the coach's son?
Who is captain of
the football team,
and Riverdale High's
resident golden boy?
Or I can expose him in the
pages of the Blue and Gold.
Yeah, I can do that!
No. Spoken like a
true good girl who
always follows the rules.
Well, I don't follow rules,
I make them, and when
necessary, I break them.
You wanna help me get
revenge on Chuck,
Betty, awesome.
But you better be willing
to go full dark, no stars.
What do you say, in or out?
Excuse me.
Veronica?
Betty, what are
you guys doing here?
Don't worry about it.
I mean it, Andrews.
Hit the showers
and stay out of my way.
- Huh, B and V.
Menage a right on. Ladies.
This is disgusting.
Take it down.
Whoa, whoa. Why are
you so wound up?
It's a badge of honor,
and you're not exactly
virgin territory after your
closet date with Andrews.
Okay, that's beyond
irrelevant, Chuck. You're not
allowed to go around
humiliating girls,
for any reason, under any
circumstances, you jerk.
Look, I get you're
not a closet kind
of girl, but hey,
if you wanna ride
the Chuck Wagon,
that can be arranged.
Let's keep this simple,
so that your preppy-murderer
half-brain can grasp it.
Take.
This. The hell.
Down.
Okay, that high-toned bitch
attitude may have
worked on the betas
you dated in New York, but
you're in Bulldog territory.
But please, fight back.
You'll only make it
harder on yourself.
And in that
moment of hesitation,
you're dead.
All of you are dead.
At ease, Doiley.
I'm writing an article
for the Blue and Gold.
Hoping you can help.
Dismissed.
But stay close.
Cheryl and Archie both say
they heard a gunshot
the morning of July 4th,
but they don't know who fired.
Sherriff Keller already
asked me about this.
And like I told him,
my Scouts and I, we didn't
hear anything weird.
Well, did you
see anything weird?
A white-winged crossbill.
A long-eared owl.
Oh.
And Cheryl, sitting by
the river, soaking wet.
Psst. Archie.
Thanks to you, Archie, I'm not
the girl who cried gunshot.
You believed me when
not even my parents did.
I just told the truth.
Which is why I want
to repay your kindness.
Cheryl, truly, that's not
why I came forward.
Save the, "Aw, shucks"
for Betty.
I'm granting you
one wish, Archie.
Nothing is off the table.
Except for my body.
Jason would want you
to be rewarded.
Actually, there is one thing.
Hey, Josie.
I love my girl Cheryl,
so I am doing her this solid.
She said that you needed help
with your music since
Ms. Grundy bailed on you.
The Pussycats are
playing my mom's event,
The Taste of Riverdale,
and we are rehearsing
every night this week.
Come. Observe.
Learn.
This week I'm, uh,
I'm grounded.
Yeah, okay, not your problem.
I'll make it work.
Okay.
Thank you.
Hey, I've been
meaning to ask.
How was your date last night?
I like the looks of that boy.
The more handsome
on the outside, the more
rotten on the inside.
What's that supposed to mean?
Nothing, just that
he's not really my type.
This is Betty. Can I take it?
Yeah.
Hello?
This story is bigger
than we thought.
I started asking around,
to see if what happened to you
happened to anyone else,
and if anyone would
go on record.
- I will. 100%.
- Okay.
It's five guys
on the football team.
Chuck and his posse.
Ethel was about to tell us...
One day last year,
Chuck and I talked in
the library for 10 minutes.
I helped him
with a Pre-Cal problem,
and nothing happened.
But the next day, he...
He started telling people that
I let him do stuff to me.
Like, sex stuff.
And then he...
Or one of his goons,
wrote, "Sloppy seconds"
on my locker.
Yes, yes, we've all heard
your tragic origin story.
I'm so, so sorry, Ethel.
That's horrible.
Not as horrible as being
a suspect in your own
brother's torture-murder case,
but we all have our crosses.
In the meantime, River Vixen
practice starts in five
minutes, sluts, so...
They're ruining our lives,
and to them it's just a game.
- They keep score and...
- Wait, what do you mean,
keep score?
Each conquest earns
them points.
They keep track
in some secret playbook.
Okay, we have to talk
to Weatherbee.
I already tried.
Weatherbee said that
he didn't find anything.
Okay, we need
undeniable proof.
Proof of what, Nancy Drew?
That boys will be boys?
And that playbook reeks
of suburban legend.
How would you know, Cheryl?
Because, Frida Shallow,
before he died, my brother
was co-captain of
the football team with Chuck,
and Jason never
mentioned it, and he never
would've allowed it.
Okay, well, I never
met your brother,
but I'm not lying about
what happened to me.
And Ethel's not lying.
And proof or no proof,
book or no book,
I am going scorched earth
on these privileged,
despicable miscreants.
You wanna get caught
in that backdraft, Cheryl?
Call me, or any of these
beautiful, young, strong,
intelligent women...
"slut"
one more time.
Right. Yeah, I'm gonna take
care of the check, all right.
Save me some.
- What the hell, man?
- I saw the way
you looked at me.
During Grizzly training.
You're hiding something.
It's Scoutmaster Doily.
- He's lying.
- About what?
The gunshot. It was him.
He was teaching us
how to shoot targets.
Dilton Doiley shot
the gun on July 4th?
He's a hardcore survivalist.
He says if we don't protect
ourselves, no one will.
Melody's our technique queen.
And you're the songwriter?
I would love to...
Love to what?
That's the real question.
What exactly you expect
to get out of this experience.
Short version.
I just want to hear
you guys play my songs.
Making them better.
Recording them.
So, you feel
qualified to write songs
for the Pussycats?
Yeah.
- For divas of color?
- No.
Maybe, maybe.
Look, this isn't LA or
New York, this is Riverdale,
and people's minds are
opening up, but do you
have any idea
how much hate mail my mom got
when she was elected mayor?
I campaigned for
your mom, I get it.
No, no, no, baby, you don't.
I mean do you know why
we're called the Pussycats?
Because we have to claw
our way into the same rooms
that you can just waltz into.
So, if you think that you
can write my experience...
- Josie?
- It's okay, Valerie.
She's right.
Good.
Ethel.
Betty, you know
Trev Brown, right?
Valerie's brother?
- Hey, what's up?
- Hey.
He used to be on
the football team.
But I quit.
When I saw Chuck's playbook.
And I may know where it is.
Football players behaving
badly, what else is new?
Steubenville, Glen Ridge.
The coach's son being
the ringleader. I mean, just
how depraved is this town?
Color me impressed.
A B and E with B and V.
What would your holy roller
mother say about this, Betty?
What are you
doing here, Cheryl?
And where did you get
those thigh-high boots?
They're amazing.
Trev told Valerie, who told
Josie, who told Ginger,
who told Tina, who told me.
And I thought
I would help out.
Help? Or derail
our investigation?
Get over yourself, Betty.
Hey guys, get in here.
Trev was right.
They didn't even
bother to hide it.
New girl? Is that
what I'm reduced to?
- Nine points?
- Better than "Big girl."
Seven point five.
Polly's in this book...
Next to Jason's name.
I'm so sorry, Betty.
- This isn't...
Jason would never...
- It's right there, Cheryl!
God.
Your brother hurt my sister.
This is what guys like Jason
and Chuck think about women.
We're objects
for them to abuse.
And when they're done with us,
they shame us into silence.
They have zero remorse
for the lives they destroy.
Maybe I don't know Jason.
I'll take a picture.
We'll show it to Weatherbee.
It'll be the perfect cover
for your expose, Betty.
Yeah, but... No. These girls
deserve justice, don't
you think, Cheryl?
You want vengeance?
You wanna go full dark,
no stars, Veronica?
I'm with you.
And I have a plan.
Val, you are such a poet,
but these lyrics,
they don't make sense.
What is the hook? I mean,
I need a line that catches.
- I hear that.
- This...line.
- I've been struggling.
- What about,
"Paintings in the wind"?
How about,
"Paintings on her skin"?
I kinda dig that.
All right. Let's, uh,
take it from the top.
One, two, one, two, three.
♪ Paintings on her skin
Colors in her hair
♪ Come around the corner,
make you stop and stare
♪ She don't pay no mind,
'cause she don't really care
♪ What you think about her,
think about her
♪ I don't care what
you want me to be
♪ 'Cause it ain't for you,
no it's all for me ♪
That was... That was so good.
What else you got?
Uh, I was thinking
maybe we could invert
the second and third verses.
Seduce Scarlet doesn't
suit you, dear.
It's Polly's.
I'm borrowing it.
Polly grew up too fast.
I don't want you to make
the same mistake.
Well, I like it.
It makes me feel...
powerful.
You coming with us
to the Mayor's shindig?
No.
I'm going over to Veronica's
to study for a test.
I don't want you associating
with a girl like that.
A bad girl, you mean?
Get used to it, Mom.
She's my friend.
Here. Pink Perfection.
It's more you.
Hey, Chuck.
Can I sit?
Not if you wanna
discuss Veronica.
Only insofar as...
I've been thinking lately...
How I wanna be more...
like her.
You wanna be a bad girl?
Maybe.
Like your sister Polly was?
Oh, yeah, Jason told us
all about Polly.
You know, prissy prude by day,
freak in the sheets by night.
Bad girls have
more fun, right?
Yeah.
Maybe you can show me.
Yes. Yes, I...
I can do that. Um...
- When?
- Tomorrow night.
- Uh, your place or mine?
- Ethel's.
She and her
parents will be out.
She'll leave us a key.
We're friends.
And she has a pool...
And a hot tub.
I'll be there.
Definitely. Um.
Hey, and don't worry.
I'll be gentle.
- Can't wait.
- Hmm.
Welcome home, Ferris.
Sneaking out, breaking curfew.
Getting into fights.
Dad, don't freak out, okay.
I was with Josie, helping
the Pussycats with a song
they're doing at that
Taste of Riverdale thing.
- And I was hoping
you would let me go.
- No, Archie.
You don't get to go
wherever you want,
whenever you want,
and damn what
anyone else says.
Dad, this is the first time
a song I worked on is gonna be
performed in front of people.
On stage.
Please, let me go to this,
and then ground me for
the next six months, a year.
- We're not haggling over your
punishment, end of story.
Fine.
But you have to own it.
Own what?
Okay, if I had a football game
tomorrow night, would you
stop me from going?
No, because football you
understand. You respect.
But my music, since I told you
about it, you don't care.
You don't take it seriously.
This is not about my behavior.
This is about your behavior.
We're done here.
You're not Betty.
Betty and I talked it over,
and we decided it's time
to stop fighting over Archie,
and start learning to share.
- Nice.
- Isn't it?
It gets very, very hot.
Come on.
Let's get wet.
Uh, should we wait
for Betty to get here first?
Betty couldn't make it.
So she sent me instead.
Welcome all, to the first
annual Taste of Riverdale.
As a lead-up to our
75th anniversary jubilee,
this event proves
that Riverdale truly
is a town that,
when tragedy knocks us down,
we get right back up!
Bon appetit.
Well, well, well,
Hermione Lodge.
- Fred Andrews.
- You look like
you could use this.
May I try a blue cheese
slider, please?
Of course.
Hey, you're the music teacher
at the high school, right?
- Yeah.
- Hi, I'm Fred Andrews,
Archie's dad.
Can we talk?
Penelope? Clifford?
Hey. How are you holding up?
How do you think?
My son is dead, and neither
of you have done anything
to catch his killer,
except, of course,
harass my daughter.
Penelope Blossom. I thought
I might run into you.
Would you like to give me
a quote regarding the...
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. All right.
- How dare you, Alice Cooper!
Printing my son's autopsy?
He was tortured and shot,
and thrown in the river
like a piece of garbage.
Hey, hey, hey.
Leave it. Leave it.
Hey, Riverdale.
We are Josie
and the Pussycats.
Are you ready to rock?
♪ Paintings on her skin,
colors in her hair
♪ Come around the corner,
make you stop and stare
♪ But she don't pay no mind,
'cause she don't really care
♪ What you think about her,
think about her
♪ Moving through the streets,
she travels on her own,
'cause she don't need...
Are you sure it was worth
sneaking out for some
locally-sourced Munster?
I helped write that song, man.
♪ And if you try to
tell her what to do
♪ She says...
Not bad.
♪ I don't care what
you want me to be
I'd love to stay, but I got to
shake down an evil
Adventure Scout. See you.
♪ 'Cause it ain't for you,
no, it's all for me
♪ Had a lot of people
say they'd try to help
♪ But they don't know the
story, they just try to... ♪
I've heard
a lot about you.
Archie says you're great.
Very supportive.
That's very sweet of him.
I need you to tell me
the truth about something.
I know my son
has passion for music.
Does he have any talent?
See, I want to
be supportive,
but as a parent,
it's really hard to watch
your kid chase a dream
they may never catch,
when real-life opportunities
are passing them by.
Mr. Andrews, Archie...
He has talent. Unquestionably.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
He is coming to it late.
And he's got a lot
of catching up to do.
And there's an entire world
of competition out there.
Will he be able
to make a living at it?
It'd be a shame
if he didn't at least try.
♪ Nothing can shake her... ♪
You know, I gotta ask you.
What made you take such
an interest in my son?
Archie's a special kid.
Okay, we're gonna do
something a little different.
Hermione Lodge.
Park Avenue princess
to cater-waiter.
Alice Cooper. No longer
lactose intolerant, I see.
How's Veronica?
Oh. You don't even
know, do you?
The things that they're saying
about your daughter at school?
- What things?
- Slut-shaming.
That's what they call it
when sluts get shamed.
You know, you really
have to keep an eye
on girls like Veronica.
They so easily can
get out of control.
- What is that?
- Muscle relaxer.
Mix it with booze and it
lowers your inhibitions.
Hello, truth serum.
Maybe we should
slow it down a little?
It's fine. Right, Chuck?
You don't want to
slow down, do you?
Oh, I'm 2 Fast 2 Furious,
baby.
Good.
Good boy, Chuck.
Hello, Dilton.
I talked to one
of your Scouts.
I know you fired the gun.
Which makes you both
a liar, and a public menace.
So what if I did?
I was doing
the Adventure Scouts a favor.
Somebody has to teach them
how to stand their ground.
The way this town is going...
Save it for your statement.
Which you can make
to Sheriff Keller, or to me.
I suggest the latter.
Blue and Gold
offices. Tomorrow.
What? What the hell?
Start recording.
Hey, guys. It's
really hot in here.
And getting hotter
by the minute.
Time to squeal, pig.
Tell the truth about
what happened between
you and Veronica.
We had a good time.
She had a good time.
The truth, Chuck, or so help
me, I will boil you alive.
What?
- We made out.
- And then?
And then I took her home!
And I didn't give her
a Sticky Maple.
That is all you had
to say, you ass.
And now, everyone will know.
You like shaming
people, Chuck?
- Whoa, hey...
- You like
dehumanizing them?
- Okay!
- Prissy prude by day,
freak in the sheets by night?
- No!
- Apologize.
- Hey, get this...
- Calm down.
- Say you're sorry!
- Okay!
Okay, I'm sorry!
I'm sorry for all of it!
Good job, pig.
Now, time for your reward.
A Sticky Maple of your own.
Wait! What, what?
Apologize for ruining Polly.
- What the hell? Oh, my God!
- Do it, Jason!
Say you're sorry
for destroying me.
- Apologize for what
you did to me!
- Look, I'm not Jason!
- I'm not Jason!
- Betty, that is enough!
Stop, it's over!
We did it. You did it.
You are crazy.
Oh, my God!
You're crazy as hell!
Betty?
I'm fine.
We're done here.
Dad?
Dad, what's going on?
Well, I am soundproofing
the garage.
I figure, you know, while
you're grounded, you
should at least be productive.
Practicing your music.
Dad, this is awesome.
Thank you.
I met your music teacher
last night. Yeah, Ms. Grundy?
Whoa. They did not look
like that in my day, son.
Ah, what were you
guys talking about?
You.
She believes in you, Archie.
So do I.
Quite the expose.
Whenever did you find
the time to write it?
Stayed up all night.
Couldn't sleep after...
Me neither.
Betty...
You came through for me,
in a way that no one
else ever has before.
But...
Can we talk about
what happened?
What do you mean?
The wig and everything.
How far were you
gonna take it?
- Chuck deserved it.
- You called him Jason.
- Know what? I didn't do that.
- Yeah, girl, you did.
You called yourself Polly.
It was like Dr. Jekyll,
Mistress Hyde.
You became another person.
Okay, I mean...
I remember saying Chuck
should apologize for Polly,
but not because I
thought he was Jason.
- Why then?
- Because...
I'm sick of guys like Chuck
and Jason doing horrible
things to girls like me,
you, and Polly. Okay?
Good and evil.
Light and dark.
Betty and Veronica.
Two sides of the
same Janus coin.
Given Betty's article,
Weatherbee needed
a sacrificial lamb.
Needed to make
an example of someone.
So, after Hermione Lodge
negotiated a lesser sentence
for our two avenging angels...
Next time, mija,
you come to me first.
You don't take matters
into your own hands.
Coach Clayton,
to save his job, to save
the school's reputation,
was forced to cut his own
beloved son, and his goon
squad, from the team.
An action that, though none of
us knew it at the time, would
have terrible consequences
in the weeks to come...
Thanks, Betty.
Thanks, Veronica.
Thank you, Ethel,
for going on the record.
It made all of the
difference with Weatherbee.
You're the bravest
of them all, Ethel Muggs.
Hashtag JusticeForEthel.
But one thing was
certain, Betty and Veronica,
now B&V,
and maybe forever,
had been forged.
They walked through the fire,
and survived.
Whoever killed Jason hurt him.
Maybe Jason hurt people, too.
If he hurt Polly, I'm sorry.
Archie?
I, uh...
I wanted to thank you
for talking to my dad.
I meant what I told him.
I think it could
really happen for you.
So...
Does this mean we can
start our lessons
back up again?
We crave absolutes.
They comfort us,
but life is infinitely more
complex than that.
If you publish a story
saying I fired that gun,
my life will be ruined.
I'll be banished from
the Adventure Scouts,
and charged
with a misdemeanor.
So, what if I have
a better story?
If I tell you what I know,
promise me the gunshot
stays between us.
You have our word.
As journalists.
I saw something
at Sweetwater River.
Something nobody else saw.
Ms. Grundy's car.
By the river's edge.
She was there.
Despite all of our
recent troubles,
I would've done anything
to protect Archie.
But Dilton Doiley had just
opened Pandora's box,
and now, there was
nothing I, or anyone,
could do to save him.
Subtittle By | SupunWe |