Previously on
Riverdale...
The story is about a town,
once wholesome and innocent,
now forever changed
by the mysterious murder
of Jason Blossom
on the 4th of July.
Your father hired
the Southside Serpents
to decrease the value
of the drive-in's land.
- Where is the rest of it?
- The rest of it?
- Where are you gonna live now?
- I'll figure it out, Dad.
I always do.
I saw you, Mom.
With Fred Andrews.
Two signatures are needed
to award the contract.
Sorry, Mom, but no.
I don't want any part of it.
What's going on?
That SoDale contract? Awarded
to Andrew's Construction.
Looks like you won.
You're...
With Jason's...
You just have to help me
get out of here.
I'll go to the car
on the lost highway
off of Route 40.
Is that Jason's jacket?
We need to get Sheriff Keller
and then we need to get Polly.
What makes a
place feel like home?
Is it warmth and familiarity?
Some idealized,
make-believe TV version
of the American Dream?
Is it love and acceptance?
Or is it simple safety?
Dude.
Why'd you stab me
in the back?
Or it's none of those things.
And it's a place where
the captain of the
football team is murdered.
Or maybe it's just
a forgotten closet
under a well-trod staircase,
where it's just you
and the mice and the spiders,
like an extra
in a Wes Craven movie.
- Oh!
- Whoa.
What are you doing here?
Taking advantage
of the school's
state-of-the-art facilities.
No, really, Jughead.
What are you doing in here?
How long?
Well, since they shut down
the drive-in.
That's where
I was living before.
Why the hell are you
not living at home?
The truth is,
things aren't good at home.
- With your dad?
- Yeah.
He kind of fell off the wagon.
After your dad fired him,
to tell you the truth.
Hasn't had a job since.
He keeps promising
that he's gonna get
his act together,
but my mom couldn't take
that rollercoaster anymore,
so she grabbed Jellybean
and went to live
with our grandparents.
Come on.
God, Jug,
why didn't you tell me?
And where does your dad
think you are?
He thinks I'm couch-surfing.
Well, screw that.
Live with me.
This is temporary, man.
I'm going to figure
something out.
Just don't tell anybody.
Especially not Betty.
Betty?
She's not gonna care.
If anyone's gonna be
a snob about it,
maybe Veronica.
Right, well, exactly.
Don't tell her, either.
What's all this?
Some retail therapy
to salve my emotional wounds,
a few treasures
from Glamazon.com.
Smithers, be a love
and put those in my room.
Veronica, the nest egg
that your father left us
barely covers the rent
of this apartment.
We can't live
beyond our means.
Are you sure, Mother?
Not even with
your cushy new job
working for your high-school
boyfriend?
My mom and dad
don't want to get
the police involved.
They don't want anyone
to know that she ran away,
or about her
shameful condition.
Please.
What decade is this?
Also, since she knew
where Jason's getaway car was,
they're afraid people
might think that she burned it
and that if she did...
She could be the murderer,
trying to cover her tracks.
Who did burn the car, then?
Sheriff Keller
says it's possible
someone was following us.
Oh, my God.
Honestly, guys,
we should just move.
Guys, what if Polly's
really hurt?
What if whoever killed Jason
is coming after her next?
Betty, even though
your parents don't want to,
maybe you should
go to the police.
Second it. We can talk
to my dad together
about how he has
to be discreet.
No offense, Kev,
but your dad answers
to a higher authority
than God, the Blossoms.
They're the first people
that he would tell.
And if there's anyone
to keep this a secret from,
it's the Blossoms.
They'd twist it around
and go after Polly
out of spite.
How can we help?
Tell us, B,
and we'll do it.
Hey, Juggy.
Remember before how you said
you didn't want Betty knowing
where you were living?
Is that because
you and Betty...
We may have had a moment...
It's totally cool, I get it.
No worries,
I'm just curious.
Hey, I've been thinking
about your situation,
and I talked to my dad.
He said he's willing
to give your dad
a second chance,
but only if FP wants it.
He's gonna call him.
But I think you should
talk to him, too.
Between the two of us,
I think we can really
make this thing happen.
Did I just notice
Riverdale High's
very own Holden Caulfield
put his arm around you?
Okay, so these past
couple of days,
I haven't been
in a great place, emotionally.
And Jughead was really
there for me...
Oh, my God. Swoon!
Okay, in that case,
if he helped my girl
navigate some
turbulent waters,
well then,
Veronica Lodge approves.
Thatta girl.
Come on,
let's go find your sister.
Mrs. Blossom,
we've got forensics
going over every inch
of that car.
We're this close to a break
in your son's case.
Speaking of breaks,
what's a big one worth
to you, Mother?
Letting me be
a River Vixen again?
What on earth
are you talking about, Cheryl?
I have information you...
Both of you,
would find interesting
vis-a-vis my brother's case.
But first,
the Vixens are mine.
And I want your permission
to reclaim them.
- Good Lord, fine.
So, Ginger texted me while
I was in the ladies' room.
It seems that crazy bitch,
Polly Cooper,
escaped from some looney bin,
the same night Jason's car
was torched.
So let me do the math for you.
Polly escaping plus
Polly torching Jason's car
equals she's Jason's killer.
Covering her tracks,
trying to go underground,
like the vicious, cold-hearted
murdering mean girl
that she is.
Oh, and I just tweeted this
out to all of my minions,
so the pressure's on,
Sheriff Keller.
- You guys, oh, my God.
- What?
Cheryl just tweeted
#PollyCooperKilledMyBrother,
#NowhereToHide,
#SharpenYourPitchforks.
Oh, no.
We need to find Polly
before the Blossoms do.
The prodigal son returns.
How you doing?
You look good.
- I'm hanging in there.
- Yeah?
I came by to ask...
If you would consider
going back to work
with Fred Andrews.
Yeah, he called me.
I said no.
He fired me, Jughead.
What kind of man would I be
if I went back, hat in hand?
For starters?
A man with a job,
trying to fix his family.
Talk to your mom.
She's the one
who gave up on us,
took your sister.
Can you please
just go see Mr. Andrews?
He's willing to give you
another chance.
Oh, he's willing, huh?
That's generous of him,
after all the crap
he pulled on me.
Dad, don't you want to see
our family back together?
Mom and Jellybean
could come home.
I could come home.
It's not too late.
Okay, the Sisters of
Quiet Mercy are due north.
The getaway car was west,
on the Old Route 40.
The closest bus station
is east,
headed towards Sweetwater.
If Polly wanted
to leave Riverdale
without anyone seeing her,
she probably
would've left through--
Right here.
Eversgreen Forest.
Hey, all this stuff
with your sister,
I'm sorry you had to go
through that,
and I wasn't there
to help you.
It's okay, Arch,
you're here now.
So how's the cold war
at home?
Ugh. Horrible.
Look, I hate fighting
with my mom,
but until she's ready
to admit and to own,
that she forged my name
to help her illicit trysting
with Fred Andrews,
I can't blink, Kevin.
She needs to make
the next move.
And what if she doesn't blink?
Back in New York,
whenever I needed
to blow off some steam,
or force my mother's hand,
I'd go out on a bender,
dancing with my fave
celebrity gal-pal,
my best gay,
and some dim-witted, sexy,
disposable arm-candy.
- That's Josie, you.
- Honored.
And as for my arm-candy...
He'll do.
I'm in, I'm so in.
Should we invite Betty?
She could probably
use a distraction right now.
I think she might be
a tad busy.
Alice Cooper, where is she?
Where's Polly?
You think if I knew that,
I'd be out here
with the mosquitoes?
Face facts, Mommie Dearest,
Polly killed Jason.
She escaped from
the asylum once, who's to say
she didn't before,
say, the day
Jason got murdered?
The noose is tightening
around your murdering
daughter's neck.
- I know it,
Sheriff Keller knows it.
- Hold on now.
And I promise you,
when we find her,
and we will find her,
the entire town of Riverdale
will know, too.
Mom, is this a good idea?
I thought we were trying
to contain this.
Well, we were, Elizabeth.
But now that
the cat's out of the bag,
we're in full-on
damage-control mode.
The Blossoms have their
version of the events,
but they don't know
the whole story,
at least not yet.
And that gives us
a momentary advantage.
I don't know if I can do this.
Oh, you can, and you will.
You'll be standing right
beside me and your father,
a united front against
the holiest of backdrops.
Let's see the Blossoms
try to smear us then.
There's been a swirl
of rumors today
about our daughter, Polly.
And we're standing here
to tell you that
they're all false.
Yes, Polly was seeking
treatment in a private
care facility,
and she was under
strict observation
even at the time
of Jason Blossom's death.
When she found out
about the murder,
she was beside
herself with grief.
You see, my daughter, Polly,
is pregnant with
Jason Blossom's baby.
Polly wouldn't hurt a fly,
let alone the father
of her unborn child.
Polly, darling,
if you're watching this,
please come home.
Hey, you didn't have
to walk me home.
Uh, there's a killer
on the loose, remember?
Besides, isn't this what...
You know...
What people like us,
who've gone through
what we've gone through, do?
What is it?
I mean, besides everything.
She wouldn't have run away
if it wasn't for me, Jug.
Betty, your parents
were the ones lying to her,
and keeping her in the dark.
You did the right thing
telling her the truth.
It's funny.
This isn't the first time
Polly's run away from home.
When she was nine,
she and my mom
got in this huge fight,
and she disappeared for hours.
The whole neighborhood
was out looking for her.
How far did she get?
What?
Thank you
for walking me home.
I'll call you later.
Goodnight.
Mom? Dad?
Polly?
It's okay. I'm alone.
Mom and Dad aren't here.
Shh.
Betty, you have to help me.
Please.
How did you get up here
without anyone seeing you?
I wrote the book on getting
in and out of this house.
And Dad still hasn't fixed
the cellar door.
Polly, everyone's
worried sick,
why did you leave the home?
You could have really
hurt yourself.
I couldn't just stay there,
waiting for someone
who was never gonna show.
Jason and I, we had a plan
to go to this farm, upstate,
and raise the baby.
It's where I still want to go,
but I don't have any money,
I don't have anything.
Why don't you
just stay here?
Mom and Dad want me to give
the baby up for adoption,
they made that very clear.
And that's not what I want.
Well, this is
their grandchild, Polly.
Everyone knows
you're pregnant now.
There's no more stigma.
You don't know
what they'll do.
And I won't have my baby
raised in a home
that doesn't want it.
Polly...
Give me a few days.
I'll find you someplace safe,
here in Riverdale.
Please, Polly,
I cannot lose you again.
This is an upgrade
from the tin can
we used to work in.
Wasn't sure you were gonna
take me up on the offer.
Wasn't sure it was real.
I'm not gonna lie to you,
it wasn't my idea.
The boys came up with this.
But I probably could
have reached out before.
Look, coming back here
isn't easy for me.
But, hell, I...
I just want my son
to look at me and not see
a piece of garbage.
Feels like it might be
my last shot.
Then let's make it work.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Hermione, you remember
FP Jones from high school.
- He's gonna be
working with us.
- Hermione.
- Of course.
- It's been forever. Hi.
- Hi.
Excuse me.
Yeah, Vic, talk to me.
Look, if this is another
shake-down...
No, it's not, we're good.
Your convict husband
settled-up.
I think he got the message
after you got
our little care-package.
Why are you even here?
My son asked me to try
and go straight, okay?
You gonna make that
hard on me?
Dudley-Do-Right
doesn't know I'm a Serpent,
so I'd appreciate it
if you keep that to yourself.
Because here's the thing
about snakes.
You don't step on them,
they got no reason to bite.
Mom, Dad,
when we find Polly,
she's gonna
live with us, right?
At this point,
there's no reason to hide
or banish her, is there?
Oh, of course not, honey.
She's welcome back.
Where will the baby sleep?
Sweetie, um, we've talked
to your sister about this,
and she's agreed to put
the baby up for adoption.
Polly did?
This is a very difficult
decision for a young
mother to make,
but given the circumstances,
it's the best.
- The only...
- The only option.
Why do you ask, honey?
No reason.
Just curious.
I don't want Polly
to run away.
But if she can't
live at home, then...
I don't know,
I can rent her an apartment.
Let me talk to my mom.
No, you have your
own stuff you're dealing
with right now, V.
Betty, Polly needs doctors,
she needs prenatal vitamins...
She needs her family.
What do you want, Cheryl?
What we both want.
For the baby to be safe.
How can I help?
You can't,
I don't trust you, Cheryl.
So don't trust me.
Watch me like a hawk.
Tell me the barest minimum.
But let me help you
help Polly.
You think Polly's crazy.
I do, I think she's crazier
than a serial killer
on bath-salts, but so what?
She's carrying Jason's baby.
That trumps everything.
Do you know where she is?
If I did,
I wouldn't tell you.
- Oh, my God, you do.
- What? No.
Wow, you are literally
the worst liar
I've ever encountered.
Spare me the details, Betty.
Just tell me
how I can be of assistance
to my darling nephew or niece.
Okay, uh,
Polly needs money.
For a safe place to live.
And for medical stuff.
Cash? Is that all?
I can talk to my mom and dad.
What? No, Cheryl.
Jason's baby
is a game-changer.
We're all on
the same team now.
- Oh, how was
your first day back?
Oh, it was great.
Your dad is
the hardest-working guy
on the crew, as always.
Oh, in that case,
why don't we celebrate
to mark the occasion?
Yeah, Juggy and I
were thinking
the four of us could have
dinner or something.
Uh, tonight?
I don't know...
I'm game if you're game.
On me.
Anyway...
We spent the whole summer
fixing up that old VW bus.
Yeah.
Remember what
we called it, Fred?
The Shaggin' Wagon.
This was before
your dad had game.
Senior Year,
he started a band,
and then the girls
were all over him.
We were awful.
Yeah, yeah, we were.
Oh.
But it was great.
Best time of my life.
You know, your dad
was what is commonly known
as a BMOC, Jughead.
- Come on. The hell I was.
- In what way?
Football, for one.
He single-handedly
defeated our arch-rivals,
the Baxter High Ravens.
He doesn't care
about that stuff, Fred.
Football, sports.
Takes after his mom
in that respect,
and I mean that
as a compliment.
I'd rather see you
spending your time
writing, thinking up stories,
you still do that?
Nose in a book?
Typing away?
Yeah, yeah, Jughead works on
the school paper with Betty.
Betty?
Ooh.
Who is Betty?
Is that your girlfriend?
She's...
I wanna know
more about the band.
What was the name
of the band?
Ah, yeah.
It was called The Fred Heads.
Wait, the what now?
Yeah, that's why it doesn't
come up very often.
Oh, thanks, Pop.
Oh, come on, Fred.
This was supposed
to be my treat.
Hey, you get it next time.
Hey, excuse me. Pop?
We invited you guys out.
Let me pay.
Put your damn money away.
FP, take it easy.
You owe me this.
- Yeah, sure.
- Yeah.
Go ahead.
You get this one.
You know, if I'd have known,
I would have gotten
another milkshake.
Where are you going?
And don't say clubbing,
it's a school night.
But that's exactly
where I'm going,
and do you know why?
Because I have a Get Out
of Jail Free card.
Okay, Ronnie, enough.
Checkmate.
What do you want?
For you to admit
what you did.
Fine.
I kissed Fred Andrews.
No, Mom, the other thing.
It involves you
forging my signature
to get Fred Andrews
that stupid contract
to build on Dad's land.
Veronica, I asked you
to sign that...
You broke the law, Mom,
and you used me to do it.
When Daddy finds out,
he's gonna think
I betrayed him.
He won't, I will tell him.
Really? When?
Right now?
Because I'll cancel
my plans for that.
You know it doesn't
work that way.
In that case,
I'll talk to you later,
my friends are waiting.
Ronnie, do not
go out that door.
Veronica!
Ah!
Mmm-mmm, girl.
You better hydrate.
You practically left
your body on the dance floor.
I wish, Josie.
I wish I could leave
my body sometimes.
Leave Riverdale,
leave everything.
Is any of this helping?
Going out, going Black Swan,
any of it?
When my dad got arrested,
the police, the lawyers,
the judge, the courts,
they took everything from us.
Our houses, our cars,
our club memberships,
our yacht,
even, I'm not kidding,
the clothes off our backs.
Anyway, my mom sat me down
on the edge of my canopy bed
and she told me not to cry.
Because there was one thing
in this world
that no one could ever
take from me.
- Not ever.
- Your trust fund?
My name, Reggie.
Which, after telling me
no one would ever take it,
that is exactly what she did.
Like it meant nothing.
Like it was nothing.
Like I was nothing.
Damn, Hoss, you're good.
Way better than your dad.
Hey, does Fred
keep any beer in there?
Uh...
Dad, don't you think
it's a little late? Kinda...
Oh, yeah, yeah.
No, it's all right.
You know, I got a big day
tomorrow anyway.
Hey, Mr. Jones,
before you go,
- can I ask you a question?
- Yeah.
Earlier tonight,
you said my dad owed you.
What did you mean by that?
Hey, Archie,
why don't we quit
while we're ahead?
It's just...
I mean, it's just a question.
Did something happen
between you two?
It's ancient history,
but your dad and me, we...
We started Andrews
Construction together.
You and my dad
were partners?
He wouldn't call us that.
Anyway, we, uh...
We struggled at first.
Fred, he just had you
and your mom to provide for,
I had Jughead and Jellybean
and their mom
and hospital bills.
So I took some odd jobs
that weren't exactly
on the level.
And sure enough, one of 'em
landed me in some hot water,
and your dad was good enough
to bail me out.
But then he said
we should part ways.
That I was a liability.
Made me sign a paper
saying the bail money was him
buying me out of the company.
Never mind that my share
of the business
was worth probably
10 times that, easy.
So that was that.
He went his way,
and I went mine.
You know, I think I need
something a little harder
than beer.
Clifford and I
were so relieved
when Cheryl told us
that Polly and the baby
are safe and sound.
And money won't be
a problem, Betty.
Not now, not ever.
Not with us.
But, of course,
we don't want to just offer
financial support,
we want to give Polly
all the emotional support
that a young
mother-to-be needs.
Where is Polly staying now?
I'd rather not say yet.
You understand.
Of course, but you and Polly
are part of the Blossom
family now,
and we will protect you
ferociously.
All you have to do is trust.
Will you?
Jughead,
what your dad told us...
I had no idea.
Me neither.
Illuminating, isn't it?
My dad must've had
a good reason.
For screwing over my dad?
Are you ready to roll,
Jugs?
See you tomorrow.
I'm sorry, Ms. Lodge,
but your card's been declined.
Really?
And let me guess,
it's been reported stolen.
It has, in fact.
We're supposed
to call the cops.
Yeah, sure.
Call the cops.
We'll be happy
to tell them how old we are.
Or I could call my mom,
the mayor.
This should cover it.
Veronica, did your mom
cut you off?
She did.
- And that's a good thing?
- Oh, Reggie.
This is how
we Lodge women roll.
We feint, we parry,
we approach, we retreat.
We're like a cobra
and a mongoose dancing.
She blinked, which means,
I suspect,
that Hermione Lodge
is ready to negotiate.
Wow. Oh.
I'll sleep right here
on this couch,
you can have the bedroom.
I'm not gonna take
your bed, Dad.
It wouldn't be the first time
I crashed on this thing.
Ah, thank you.
If you stay... Are you?
You're gonna stay?
Don't be late for school.
It's all right.
I'm already way ahead
in all my classes.
Hey, I talked to Mom.
She got a job at a call center
to pay for her online classes.
I guess she's finally
going after her GED.
Jellybean is helping
her study.
By the way, Jellybean wants
to go with JB now.
She thinks it sounds cooler.
She's 10 years old and listens
to Pink Floyd on vinyl,
I don't think
she could get any cooler.
How was your jam session?
It was great,
until FP told us
you forced him out
of the company
he helped found.
That's his story,
wanna hear mine, hmm?
FP was a mess.
He was stealing
from the company
and selling stuff on the side.
All things considered,
I was pretty generous.
So generous you didn't
give him a second chance?
Of course I did.
You have no idea
how many times
I bailed that man out of jail.
Son, when someone is drowning,
you can try to save them,
but not if they're gonna
drag you down with them.
I did the best I could
for my family.
For you.
Yeah, and who cares if Jughead
ended up drowning, too.
Reporting my American Excess
card as stolen,
well-played.
I thought you might
appreciate that.
Now, mija.
I've done things to upset you.
You've done things
to upset me.
So we're gonna deal
with this exactly
as your father would like.
With a negotiation.
I'll start.
I am working with Mr. Andrews,
and yes, we are developing
feelings for each other.
But I can't tell you
what it means yet
because I don't know myself.
What about Daddy?
He has made certain decisions
that have distanced him
from me, and this family.
So I need to make
certain decisions
about my life moving forward,
what I want.
So, what, you want me
to accept your affair?
Until we get
more information, yes.
That is what
I'm asking you to accept.
Fine. Agreed.
Now, my turn.
I'm listening.
Whatever is happening
with you and Fred,
can't happen under this roof.
Agreed.
And you have to come clean
to Daddy about forging
my signature.
Lodge Industries
needs to partner
with legitimate businesses,
not criminals.
Understood.
I don't want Daddy thinking
I betrayed him.
I will tell him
about the forgery.
And say it was all my doing.
And in the meantime,
the online shopping,
the clubbing,
all that stops.
- Yes?
- Yes.
- Hey.
Uh, what's up?
I'm going to need you to come
down to the station with me.
Call my dad.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Of course.
Forensics came back
on the car.
Despite the fire,
we were able to pull a pair
of prints off the trunk.
Yours and Betty's.
This is, of course,
no surprise.
But what did surprise me
was this.
Your prints were on file
from an incident that happened
six years ago,
where you spent some time
with the Riverdale Juvenile
Delinquent Center for...
"Attempting to burn down
Riverdale Elementary School."
I was playing with matches,
and that's a pretty tenuous
connection for a sheriff.
Well, Principal Weatherbee
also allowed me
to have a look
at your school records.
You have a long and
rough history, Mr. Jones.
Bullied a lot.
Yeah, my name is Jughead.
By the football team,
in particular.
I can only assume that would
have included Jason Blossom.
So how about this?
How about you tell me
your whereabouts
on the week of July 11th?
This is crazy.
You think I...
Jughead. A kid like you,
raised on the wrong side of
the tracks by a deadbeat dad,
bullied by kids
like Jason Blossom.
Who wouldn't want
to lash out at that?
I'm not talking
to you anymore.
I want a lawyer.
Cheryl, you've called Polly
a party girl.
Have you seen her take drugs?
Firsthand?
Um... I'm not sure, why?
Due diligence.
We wouldn't want
an unfit mother
raising our grandchild now,
would we?
No, of course not.
I didn't do it, Betty,
you have to believe me.
Of course, I was with you,
and I know who you are.
Those Paradise Lost kids
went to death row
because they wore black
and they listened
to Metallica.
I don't wanna become
a scapegoat.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
All the evidence against you
is circumstantial.
We're gonna get you
out of here.
Is my dad here yet?
Archie's here with his dad.
They're talking
to the Sheriff.
No one knows
where your dad is.
Jughead's not helping
himself in there.
I asked him for an alibi,
and he just gave me lip.
He was working for me.
Yeah, the week
of July 11th, was it?
Yeah, I had him tear down
some drywall for me.
You can provide me
with documentation
to support that?
I have to check my time cards.
Jughead!
I'm sorry.
I came as soon
as I got your messages.
My phone,
the friggin' battery.
I forgot to plug it in
last night.
- What the hell happened?
- Nothing.
It's fine now.
Mr. Andrews took care of it.
What jacked-up crap
did they accuse you
of in there, huh?
Those bastards trying
to throw you in jail
like they did your old man?
Well, screw that.
I will rip Keller a new one
for trying to pull that...
- FP, settle down.
- Hey! Hey!
This is my son,
he is my son, Fred!
You'd do the same
for your boy.
Dad.
Don't make things worse.
Please.
Yeah.
Yeah, all right, then.
You, uh,
coming home with me?
He can stay with us,
Mr. Jones.
We already offered.
Is that what you want?
Maybe that's for the best.
If you don't mind, Fred.
Whatever you want, FP.
It's between the two of you.
I'll go with you, Dad.
Son, listen to me.
I'm gonna do what you want,
get my act together.
I'm gonna get your mom
and Jellybean home
so we're all
under the same roof.
I promise. But I...
I just need a little time
to do that.
Not a lot, not long,
a month, two at the most.
Hey.
And then we'll be back
on track, all right?
You...
You believe that, don't you?
Yeah, I believe you, Dad.
All right.
Any minute now.
How do you feel?
Partnering with
Andrews Construction
was the right decision
to make.
And your father will either
see that or he won't.
Either way, I can live
with the consequences.
Hello.
You're receiving
a call from
Penitentiary.
Will you accept the charges?
I'll accept the charges.
Looks like
you've done this before.
Yeah, well, FP's got
his tricks, I got mine.
Maybe I should've given him
another chance back then.
Either way,
Jughead doesn't deserve
what's happening to him.
It's the least I can do.
The Blossoms
should be here soon.
Once we've talked
things through with them,
we'll call Mom and Dad.
Are you nervous?
I'm thankful.
At the home,
the Sisters said each of us
had a guardian angel.
You're mine, Betty.
Cheryl...
I'm so sorry about Jason,
I know how much you loved him.
And he always talked
about how much he loved you.
Cheryl, where are
your mom and dad?
You have to leave. Now.
My parents, I don't think
they want to help you.
What are you talking about?
They want you
out of the picture, Polly.
It's not safe
for you with them.
for JayJay's baby.
Where am I supposed to go?
I can't go back to the attic.
No.
You don't have to, Polly.
And don't worry
about my mom, Betty,
she'll want to help.
Of course you can stay.
As long as you need.
Anything for
Alice Cooper's daughters.
Thank you, Mrs. Lodge.
- And thank you, Veronica.
- Yeah.
You're welcome, girls.
And please, now that we're
going to be roommates, Polly,
it's Hermione.
Come, sit,
make yourself at home.
I'm sorry about my dad,
and your dad.
I'm not giving up
on him, Arch.
Not yet.
You think he'll show up
for work tomorrow?
You never know. I hope.
Hope.
A word so close to home,
and as tricky.
As much as we wanted
Jason's killer caught,
and the town, our home,
to feel safe again,
with every day that passed,
our hopes dimmed
more and more.
There's that old,
cliched saying,
"It's darkest
before the dawn."
But sometimes...
There's just darkness.