Previously on Riverdale...
You know that SoDale contract?
It was awarded to Andrews Construction.
Mr. Andrews still doesn't
know that Daddy is the buyer?
I asked around about those
bruisers going after your crew.
Pretty sure we both know
who has business in Montreal.
Hiram, why would he even...
Maybe he got a whiff of your
little romance with Freddy Andrews?
When my father got arrested,
I made a pact to become a better person.
You're the bravest of
them all, Ethel Muggs.
You hate the Blossoms
and now Polly is pregnant with his baby.
Polly is moving home.
I will not be party to raising
a child that has Blossom blood.
Thicker than blood.
More precious than oil.
Riverdale's big business is maple syrup.
Since the town's founding,
one family has controlled
its lucrative syrup trade,
the Blossoms.
They were a part of the
fabric of our daily lives...
Rich or poor, old or young,
we consumed Blossom
syrup by the bucket.
That sickly, sweet
smell was inescapable.
The death of Jason Blossom
precipitated a crisis.
With the heir apparent gone,
who would inherit the
family business one day?
Certainly not Cheryl.
It was a question that brought
the wolves to Riverdale.
And now, the Blossoms
were circling the wagons
against possible attack,
from within their own ranks.
Polly won't answer my calls or e-mails.
I mean, I get that she
doesn't want to talk to my dad,
but what did I do wrong?
Nothing.
We'll figure it out.
Come here.
Up and at 'em, breakfast is ready.
I'm not hungry.
Oh, enough is enough, Elizabeth,
we have a big week ahead of us.
The Blossoms have always
been a thorn in our side,
ever since, according to
your milquetoast father,
Great-Grandpappy Blossom
killed Great-Grandpappy Cooper.
Well, it's about time
someone brings them to heel.
I'm writing a searing, no-holds-barred
takedown of their clan.
And you think that's
going to bring Polly home?
Maybe, maybe not,
but it'll make me feel better.
Word has it that the
Blossom board of trustees
has descended upon Riverdale
like a cabal of vampires.
Why? Now, that's a story.
I just need to find a way in.
The lawyers are coming over this week
to take our statements
for your dad's hearing.
We're both gonna have to
testify on your father's behalf.
What if they ask about what he did?
Embezzling all that money?
Am I going to have to lie?
Well... We might have to
shade the truth a bit, Ronnie.
Mom?
Baby, I have just made a mess of things.
Your father found out about Fred and me.
Someone went to him
before I got a chance to say anything...
Oh, my God, Dad knows?
Yes, and on top of that,
the Blossoms are still
after the drive-in land,
and Fred still doesn't
know that we own it.
Maybe it's time you tell
Mr. Andrews the truth.
And risk having him
walk off the project?
We've bet everything we have
on the SoDale construction.
Mom,
this is a small, gossipy town.
You need to tell Fred about the land
before someone else does.
Archie.
If music be the food of love,
play on, play on.
Did you know this
week's the official start
of maple syrup season?
I... No, I didn't.
Well, it is.
And every year, we host
a tree-tapping ceremony,
a tradition that honors
the Blossom bloodline.
Our heritage.
Sounds cool.
It is. Beyond.
It's also incredibly exclusive.
Family and inner circle only.
Wanna be my date?
The maple-tapping's something Jason and
I have done together since we could walk.
It was our extra-special thing.
But I...
I can't face it alone.
If you came,
as my escort,
I think I could get through it.
Cheryl, I would love to
help, but I have a girlfriend.
Maybe invite Kevin? Or Reggie?
You don't get it, do you?
I don't want Kevin or Reggie.
I want you.
You defended me to Sheriff Keller
when not even my parents would.
Never mind, I'm sorry I asked.
Cheryl, hold on.
"They put me in a wooden
box as I desperately opposed.
But all my screaming was for naught.
My mouth had been sewn closed.
Curled up in bed was just a girl.
Needing Daddy's arms to hold her."
Hey, Ethel.
I just wanted to tell you
how moved I was by your poem.
It felt like you were tapping
into something pretty dark,
but also pretty real.
And I don't want to overstep...
But is everything all right, Ethel?
Things at home aren't great.
My mom and dad are fighting,
but they won't tell me about what.
It's like this really
bad thing is happening,
and there's nothing
that I can do to stop it.
Like you're trapped in
a slow-motion car crash.
Yeah, I know the feeling.
Listen, Ethel.
It sounds like you
need some cheering up.
Which happens to be a
Veronica Lodge specialty.
So...
If you're free tomorrow,
come over for lunch and pampering.
Kevin will be there.
Yeah, come on, it'll be fun.
Just please say yes.
All right, sure.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Great, I'll see you tomorrow.
So... What was that about?
Ethel's poem was a cry for help
if I ever heard one,
the likes of which I
vowed never to ignore,
not after...
Uh-oh. Do we need to sit down?
Okay, so, last year at Spence,
my best friend Katy and I kind
of terrorized this girl, Paige.
One time, we made her
drink gutter water.
Ew! Why?
Because she was there.
Because she was a misfit
and we were class-A brutal bitches.
Anyway, by December,
Paige couldn't take it anymore...
Oh, my God, did you
drive her to suicide?
What? No.
But she did transfer schools.
And went into therapy.
So now?
If I can make Ethel Muggs'
life a little better,
even for one afternoon,
I'm going to do it.
Archibald.
I was going to get Principal
Weatherbee to summon you.
Hey, Mrs. Blossom.
Have a moment to chat?
About Cheryl.
I believe she invited you
to our tree-tapping ceremony?
Yeah.
She did, and like I told her,
I don't feel comfortable going.
Cheryl tells me
you have a keen interest in music.
Is that true?
Did she tell you her
Great-Uncle Harrison
sits on the board of the
Brandenburg Music Academy?
They have an excellent
summer program, I hear.
It's amazing, crazy hard to get into.
Surely not for a talent like you.
And especially not if I put
in a word on your behalf.
Mrs. Blossom...
At Jason's memorial,
you brought me his football jersey.
So sorry for your loss, Mrs. Blossom.
I thought you might want to have this.
That was an act of kindness
on a day of despair.
You're good and decent, Archibald,
unlike most people in this town.
Mrs. Blossom, I don't know what to say.
Say you'll reconsider escorting
my daughter to the tapping.
It's just an afternoon.
And it would mean the
world to my Cheryl.
I mean, yeah. I guess
I could talk to Valerie.
I swear, Archibald,
when the light hits you just right...
I'll tell Cheryl the good news.
And I'll call Great-Uncle Harrison.
Just in time, we're celebrating.
Archie was just telling us
how he's going to some super-exclusive
music program this summer.
Maybe. If it happens, though,
it would be huge for me.
Do you have to audition for it?
Well, not exactly. Mrs.
Blossom came by earlier
and said she'd put a
good word in for me.
- Amazing.
- Terrifying.
Uh-huh.
What's she getting out of it?
I told her I'd take Cheryl
to their family's tree-tapping thing.
I already talked to Valerie,
and she's cool with it.
Cool with you being a gigolo now?
I'm doing someone a favor
for my music, Jughead.
I need to make connections
outside of Riverdale.
That's the way of the world.
It's all about connections.
But Jughead's right.
These kinds of favors
always come with a price tag.
Betty, back me up here.
I think it's a great idea.
Thank you, Betty.
Yeah, and while you're there,
would you talk to Polly for me?
I just want to make sure she's okay.
Definitely.
Thank you.
And don't worry, Ronnie,
I can take care of myself.
Famous last words, Archiekins.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
When Jason died,
I thought I'd tapped my last tree.
Now, don't be nervous.
All you have to do is
hold the bucket steady,
I'll handle the rest.
Who are all these people?
Entre nous,
they're Daddy's board of trustees.
They smell blood in the water.
That's why they're here.
They're worried Daddy's
losing his grip on the company
and they're looking for a
way to take it away from us.
They can do that?
If they all vote together, they can.
When Jason died, it was a PR debacle.
And now, here's Polly,
pregnant and unwed.
It's no wonder they've descended upon us
like some biblical plague.
"Nearly 100 years ago, Grandfather
Blossom came to this sacred maple grove.
The annual tapping ceremony
portends each season's bounty."
Now, I've performed this
ceremony many times in my life.
My son Jason, when he came
of age, performed it as well.
In his place,
I put forth my daughter Cheryl.
Hey.
You can do this in your sleep.
- Bravo!
- Well done!
Good shot. Nice.
Mrs. Lodge, this Quiche
Lorraine is to die for.
Ethel,
you haven't eaten at all.
Oh. Sorry. I just...
I'm not really hungry.
Anything we can help with?
Uh, my parents...
All they do is yell at each other.
My parents are fighting right now, too.
It's terrible.
I think my dad had some
bad luck with our savings.
Now my mom says we're going
to have to sell the house.
My dad is just so...
Crushed.
I wish there was something
I could do to help him.
Girl, we have a lot more
in common than I thought.
We lost our place at the Dakota.
Look, being ruined sucks.
But you have your
family and you have us.
You've got this, Ethel Muggs.
"Muggs"?
Uh, it's Dutch.
We lost the third "G"
when my Grandpa Manfred came over.
Archibald! Come join us
before the snow starts again.
Three, two, one.
Polly.
Betty's worried about you.
Why won't you call or e-mail her?
She fought for you, Polly,
and now you're treating
her like she's the enemy.
Polly, come along.
Tell Betty that she
shouldn't worry, okay?
Veronica, there's something
that you need to know
- about that Muggs girl.
- What?
Her father, Manfred Muggs,
invested with your dad.
And it's probable that they lost a lot
when your father was
arrested. Maybe everything.
Mom, they're being
kicked out of their house,
their home.
Well, from what I've been told,
the Muggs family is going to testify
against your father.
They should.
How many, Mom?
How many families like Ethel's?
It's the risk of doing
business with your father.
Could Mr. Andrews lose everything,
for doing business with you and Dad?
I'm not sure.
My God.
I don't buy this dog-and-pony
show for a second.
Cliff can't control his own family,
let alone the company.
Agreed.
And if he tries to put Cheryl
forward as a successor...
Do you remember what
she did at the funeral?
- Crocodile tears.
- Hey.
Archie, you don't have to.
No, Cheryl loved Jason.
What was she meant to do
at his funeral, not cry?
And yeah, Jason was
on the football team,
but Cheryl was at
every single game, too,
doing as much to help the
Bulldogs win as he did.
Also, 4.0.
Also, she has a 4.0 grade point average.
If there's one thing that I've
learned being in Cheryl's class,
it's don't underestimate her
and don't bet against her.
Fred, we need to talk.
Oh, God.
Hiram and I,
we are the anonymous buyers.
You're working for Lodge Industries.
How do you not tell me that?
You never would have gotten involved.
You're damn straight.
Because I didn't sign up
to go into business with a
criminal like Hiram Lodge.
I'm trying to turn Lodge
Industries legitimate.
That means partnering
with people like you,
good people.
This is why Cliff Blossom
bought out my crew?
Sent thugs to beat up teenagers?
Clifford didn't send those thugs.
Hiram did.
He was trying to stop us.
He found out about you
and me from Clifford.
So you have dragged me into a war
between Hiram and
Clifford, that's great.
I know you're angry.
And I know that I have
no right to ask this...
But please stay on this project.
If you jump ship, I can't
start over with someone else.
So, I do the grunt work
while your husband's
taking potshots at me
and you're playing both sides?
The whole time?
I gotta take a walk.
Archibald, do you know,
when Cheryl told me
that she wanted you to come with us,
I was a little taken aback.
Your father and I haven't
been seeing eye-to-eye lately.
I came for Cheryl, Mr. Blossom.
And because I'm grateful for
what Mrs. Blossom is doing for me.
The music academy, you mean?
Yeah, that would be quite a feather
in your cap, now, wouldn't it?
You know, we can be extremely generous,
Archibald, to the right people.
Now later this week, we're
hosting a banquet for the board
at the Belmont Lodge.
It's a simple thing, a little dinner,
chit-chat, dancing.
We would love you to
attend as Cheryl's escort.
You two make quite the pair.
Oh, I'm honored, Mr.
Blossom, really, but...
But nothing.
You have to come, I'm wearing viridian.
He'll need a proper suit,
don't you think, Daddy?
I'll have my tailor fit you.
If that's not a problem?
No. No, no, it's just...
I'm an Andrews, Mr.
Blossom, like you said.
My dad works construction,
a fancy banquet's not really our thing.
That's precisely why you should come.
People like you are
the bedrock of our town.
You're hard workers.
Plus, I need a dance partner.
We won't take no for an answer...
Archiekins.
Who would have predicted this?
Archie Andrews is our
fox in the henhouse.
Tell us about Polly.
How is she? Did she seem okay?
The Blossoms are treating her great.
But, Betty, I don't
think she's coming back.
I don't think she wants to.
That doesn't make any
sense. That's not Polly.
She made her choice.
We have to learn to live with that.
No. I know my sister. She
wouldn't do that to us.
Something else is going on.
What else did you see, Archie?
When you were in the
sticky, red thick of it?
Anything about the board?
Cheryl said that they're worried...
That after all the scandal
with Jason and Polly,
that they might try and steal
the company from Mr. Blossom.
Well, do you hear that, Betty?
This is our story. A hostile takeover.
No wonder the trustees are in town.
The Blossom empire is crumbling.
Okay, but, Mom,
if you write a story attacking them
while Polly's still in Thornhill...
Enough about Polly.
I mean it.
She's the one that betrayed us,
not the other way around.
Obviously she's jealous...
Cheryl,
can we have a word?
Scatter, my Vixens.
Yes, Betty? What is it?
Polly.
Look, I don't know what kind of Stockholm
syndrome spell you've cast on her,
but I want to talk to my sister.
Let's not fight.
Especially not when we
should be celebrating.
Why? What happened?
Haven't you heard?
Dr. Patel just confirmed
it this morning.
Polly is having twins.
Bless our Blossom genes!
And she didn't call to tell me.
Hostages aren't normally allowed
to make outgoing calls.
Can you please just give
her a message for me?
As long as it doesn't upset her.
Tell her she should call our mom.
She's trying really hard to hide it,
but I can tell she's really,
really hurt and upset.
- I'll pass your message along...
- Thank you.
If I remember.
Cheryl.
That was a joke, you hobo.
Of course I'll give
her your message, Betty.
But no promises that
she'll care or respond.
Okay, Ethel,
open your eyes.
What is happening?
I was purging my closet,
thinking how you would look magnificent
in some of these.
Here, try this on.
This is... This is so nice.
And I love this. It is so you, Ethel.
Ronnie, I can't take all this.
I want you to have it.
These things...
My dad gave them to me.
He always brought home gifts
whenever he did something wrong.
As a way to make up for it, I guess.
Did it work?
What girl is immune to the
charms of a Givenchy bag?
And I still wear these
pearls he gave me.
Okay, but...
You don't have to do anything.
Give me anything.
I just want to be friends.
Me, too, Ethel.
Mr. Andrews! Nice haircut.
You're looking extremely DILF-y today.
Is Archie home?
Cheryl, yes.
Um, come on in.
The Ice Woman cometh.
Hey, Cheryl.
As a maj thank-you for coming
to the maple banquet with me tomorrow,
I wanted to give you this.
An '84 Les Paul.
In our signature color.
You're welcome.
Okay. That's all. I'm going now.
My claustrophobia acts
up in small houses.
See you tomorrow.
I'd give that back if I were you.
Dad, come on. The Blossoms,
they're helping me get into
that summer music program.
Like, the best in the country.
And since when did the Blossoms
ever give a damn about you, Archie?
Well, they think I have potential, Dad.
He's also pimping himself out to Cheryl.
The Blossoms tried to run
our business into the ground.
Maybe if you tried
talking to Mr. Blossom...
I tried talking to him, Archie,
he laughed in my face.
Don't think for a second that the
Blossoms are looking out for you.
They're using you, Archie.
They look at us like we're
dirt under their shoe.
I'm over it.
What's this?
The biggest story we've ever broken.
A tell-all expose on the Blossom clan
and all of their glorious corruption.
Um, would you mind telling me
what your mother is talking about?
It's time that they finally answer
to everything that they've done to us,
including taking Polly.
By the way, Polly's living
with the Blossoms now,
so congratulations, you've
finally got what you wanted.
She's officially out of our lives.
I'm not publishing
your personal vendetta.
Well, it's a good thing I
don't need your permission.
What did you do, Hal?
Well, you kicked me out.
So, now, I'm kicking you out.
If we expose the Blossoms, maybe...
Just maybe, we might
have a chance in hell
to get our daughter back.
You are done here, Alice. You're fired.
Fine, Hal.
What?
I want my daughter back, you bastard!
Mom!
Black piping for the velvet, of course.
I'll take measurements for the pants.
Uh, before we do that...
Could I talk to you, Mr. Blossom?
Things aren't going
great at my dad's company.
And I know you two have
been at odds recently.
But I was wondering, instead of
helping me with that music school, if...
Maybe you could help my dad.
Are you negotiating on
behalf of your father?
No, no, I'm impressed.
In fact, I'm trying to imagine
if Jason would ever have
given up something like that for me,
and I don't believe so.
It speaks to your character, son.
But I'll tell you what,
we've already called the
Brandenburg Music Academy.
And they're very excited
to meet you, by the way.
Let's just get through
this banquet, all right?
Sit down man-to-man
and discuss what I can
do for Fred Andrews.
Is it satisfactory?
It's more than satisfactory.
My parents are unbelievable, Jug.
Polly is locked up in that house
like a character out of Jane Eyre,
and what are they doing?
Changing each other's login accounts
and throwing bricks through windows.
I wish I'd seen that.
Okay, I'm sorry, that's not funny.
It's like, you know
how, in a time of crisis,
people either come
together or fall apart?
It feels like we're falling apart.
And the way things
are going, pretty soon,
the Coopers, we're not
gonna exist anymore.
And there's nothing
I can do to stop that.
Betty, don't do that.
Don't give up.
Your family is definitely
splintering right now,
but it won't fall apart, because of you.
Because you're holding them together.
You're so much stronger
than all of the white noise.
You're stronger than your mother,
you're stronger than your father.
You're holding this family together.
So don't.
Don't let go.
I won't.
Valerie, hi.
I thought you should know,
Cheryl poured some
insane poison into my ear
about how close you two are getting.
She legit thinks she's going to
steal you away from me or something.
- No, she doesn't.
- Yes, she does.
And I don't blame her.
The new guitar, the new suit?
The Blossoms are buying you.
For one night, if it helps my dad
and gets me into that music program...
Wouldn't you rather earn
your place at that table?
With your music?
All the Blossoms are doing
is opening a door for me.
What would you do if
you were in my place?
If you have to ask,
then you don't know me at all, Archie.
Oh, my God, did you hear?
Remember when you went
swooping in to save Ethel,
'cause you thought
she might be suicidal?
Oh, no. She didn't...
No, but her dad did.
He accidentally swallowed a
whole bottle of sleeping pills.
He's going to be okay,
but that's why Ethel's
been so sad lately.
Now, everybody knows...
We were tested this year.
As a town, as a company,
mainly as a family.
And it may not have been Jason's hand
that staked the maple this year,
but it was the hand of hope.
Don't think they're
being nice or genuine.
They wanted me to fail
at the tree-tapping.
But you're going to help with all that.
I'll do whatever I can.
Archibald, have a word?
I'll be right back.
I just wanted to let you know
that I've decided to help your father.
You did? You will?
Well, you've helped our family.
Cheryl, especially.
You fit in so well.
I think you and your father
have a very bright future with us.
Thank you, Mr. Blossom.
Oh. "Clifford", please.
And just so you know,
you don't have to keep doing me favors.
I like Cheryl.
And I'm happy to be here
for her, as a friend.
You know, I'm going
to be honest with you.
Cheryl's a bright girl,
but the Blossom board,
they're very skeptical
of having her play an
active role in the company.
Now, someone with your stock
and character by her side,
tempering her more erratic behavior...
You know, it's about...
Creating a picture.
The right picture.
Having you with us, with Cheryl,
it tells a very appealing story.
Which is something I think we
could all use right about now.
You'll help us, won't you?
Excuse me, Mr. Blossom,
may I have this first dance with Archie?
I think that's an excellent idea.
Polly, can we talk about
what's going on here?
Just keep dancing.
And smiling.
Betty keeps asking Cheryl about me,
she needs to stop.
As long as she's worried about
you, Polly, she'll never stop.
Yes, she will...
If I tell you the real
reason I'm at Thornhill.
The Blossoms had something
to do with Jason's death,
I'm sure of it.
They threatened him
and I'm gonna prove it.
Is that why you keep blowing Betty off?
It has to be believable.
And I don't want her
trying to rescue me.
Can you please tell her that for me?
- I'm so done with this!
- Do not make a scene.
- No, I'm done. I'm done!
- Not now.
Polly, will you excuse me?
Betty.
Veronica, hey.
Mom, these are my friends.
This is Betty and this is Veronica.
Mrs. Muggs.
Ethel...
We heard what happened,
and we wanted to leave
these flowers with you.
That's very kind. Thank you.
Please don't...
Don't thank me.
We're just so glad Mr.
Muggs is going to be okay.
And we'll see you at school, Ethel?
You don't need to do this, Vee.
Ethel?
Mrs. Muggs?
There's something I need to tell you.
My name is Veronica Lodge.
- My father is...
- Hiram Lodge.
Hmm.
And you're showing your face here?
Mom, she's my friend.
She's not your friend, honey.
Her father is a criminal.
He's the reason Dad did this to himself.
Ronnie?
Is that true?
Yes.
And I am so sorry.
I wish I could do something.
"Sorry" isn't good enough.
You want to do
something? Tell the truth.
Your father is ruining lives.
He deserves to sit behind bars
for the rest of his miserable life.
Come on.
Cheryl.
You okay?
What did my dad say to you?
That everyone thinks I'm a train wreck?
Jason was the golden boy,
but me...
People hate me, Archie.
And at school, that's fine, whatever.
But this is my family.
Forget them, Cheryl.
Forget what they think.
I think you're awesome.
Oh, Archie,
sometimes I think you may be the
only decent person left in Riverdale.
The only person who doesn't
want something from me.
Or who doesn't want me to
apologize for who I am...
And what I want.
What are you doing?
My lipstick's maple red, by the way.
In case you're wondering
why it tastes so sweet.
They seem satisfied, but Uncle
Bedford keeps asking
about the drive-in land.
I am so close to getting that land back.
Hermione Lodge will crumble.
Who would have thought
she'd prove so resourceful?
Maybe you should've sent
her to jail instead of Hiram.
Hey.
How was your night?
I just got back from the hospital
where Ethel's dad is.
Because he tried to kill himself...
Because of what Daddy did...
And, for all I know, continues to do.
I am done lying for Dad.
Archie!
I thought it was Cinderella
that ran away from the ball,
not Prince Charming.
Cheryl, I can't do this
right now. I'm leaving.
Archie Andrews,
if you leave, the radiant sun that is
the Blossom family stops shining on you.
And everything we've given you,
including Brandenburg, disappears.
Are you sure you want to give that up?
Are you sure you want
to do that to your dad?
Cheryl, I came here as a
favor to your mom, to help you.
Oh, Archie, don't start lying now.
You may not want anything from me,
but you do from my mom and dad,
that's why you're here.
Which means,
as much as I want you to be
better than everyone else...
You're not.
You're just like the others.
I'm sorry, Cheryl...
But I can't do this anymore.
Goodbye.
Mom?
Archie just called. He talked to Polly.
She's safe.
She's okay, Mom.
She didn't choose the Blossoms over us,
she's actually there to spy on them.
You know, when I went
after this story...
I thought, in the back of my mind that,
"What if this is it?
What if this is finally the time
that she doesn't come back?"
She will, Mom.
And right now, she's
our woman on the inside.
We're going to write this story.
Come write with us
at Blue and Gold.
The school newspaper?
Yeah, that's what we are.
But I'm pretty sure that
our annual operating budget
is bigger than the Register's.
Val.
Val, hey.
Look, you were right.
About being bought and taking shortcuts.
After last night, I'm done
with the Blossoms, I am.
Good for you, Archie,
but I'm done with you.
Ever since we started
dating you've ignored me,
you've ditched me.
Val, please.
Let me make it up to you.
Sorry, Archie, but unlike
you, I won't be bought.
Just listen, Fred.
So many families have
been hurt by the Lodges.
Now, I don't want
yours to be another one.
I've decided to sell to Clifford...
Before it gets any worse.
No, you're not.
I'm going to stay with the project.
That's great.
Thank you.
Don't thank me. I'm
not doing it for you.
See, from now on,
everything we do around here
is going to be legal.
A hundred percent above board.
Agreed. Of course.
Also, my stake is 20%.
If I'm gonna put myself on the line,
I need some skin in the game.
That's a really big share.
I'm sick of you people using
me and my family as pawns.
Sure.
Anything else?
Yes.
You and me...
Whatever was going on there is over.
Now, we're just business partners.
That's it.
Right.
Ethel, I meant what I said.
I'm sorry, Ethel,
for everything my family did to yours.
It's not your fault what your dad did.
And you were there for
me when no one else was.
More than once.
Seat's not taken, if you want it.
It seemed that, for Veronica,
the sins of the father
would remain simply that.
While Archie Andrews
returned from the brink
with one more bit of news.
At the banquet, I heard Mr.
And Mrs. Blossom talking.
It sounded like Clifford
Blossom was responsible
for sending Veronica's dad to jail.
Oh, my God.
If Clifford sent Hiram Lodge to jail,
tore apart his family,
then maybe Hiram was trying
to do the same thing to him?
Yeah, by going after what
the Blossoms value most,
their family, their legacy.
That's a motive.
Winter had come early to Riverdale.
Brutal and unforgiving.
Did it work?
Are the vultures appeased?
We're not out of the woods yet.
But it would be nothing
compared to the storm
that was gathering.
A storm of chaos named...
...Cheryl Blossom.
Yes?
Good night, Cheryl.
Good night, Pollykins.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --