Our story is about
a town, a small town,
and the people who live
in the town.
From a distance,
it presents itself
like so many other small towns
all over the world...
Safe.
Decent.
Innocent.
Get closer, though,
and you start seeing
the shadows underneath.
The name of our town
is Riverdale.
And our story begins, I guess,
with what the Blossom twins
did this summer.
On the Fourth of July,
just after dawn,
Jason and Cheryl Blossom
drove out to Sweetwater River
for an early morning
boat ride.
Are you scared, Jason?
The next thing we
know happened for sure
is that Dilton Doiley,
who was leading Riverdale's
Boy Scout Troop
on a bird watching expedition,
came upon Cheryl
by the river's edge.
Jason...
Riverdale Police dragged
Sweetwater River
for Jason's body,
but never found it.
If he is dead, Hal,
I hope in those last moments
he suffered.
May Jason Blossom
burn in hell.
So a week later,
the Blossom family buried
an empty casket
and Jason's death
was ruled an accident,
as the story that Cheryl told
made the rounds.
That Cheryl dropped
a glove in the water,
and Jason reached
down to get it,
and accidentally
tipped the boat,
and panicked, and drowned.
As for us,
we were still talking about
the "July Fourth tragedy"
on the last day
of summer vacation,
when a new mystery
rolled into town.
Now brace yourself.
The apartment's small,
a pied-à-terre,
- but "quality, always."
- "Quality, always."
Plus, it's the only piece
of property in my name
and not your father's.
Ms. Hermione!
- Welcome home!
- Smithers!
Oh, you are a sight
for sore eyes.
- How was the ride?
- No traffic, thank God.
Smithers, I'd like
to introduce you
to my daughter, Veronica.
- It's a pleasure, miss.
- Hi.
- I'll get the bags.
- Would you?
Oh, and would you like
some menus, ma'am,
so you can order in?
Oh, no.
I have been craving
one of Pop Tate's
cheeseburgers
since noon.
Is his Chock'lit Shoppe
still open?
What is a Chock'lit Shoppe
and why does it sell burgers?
Subtittle By | SupunWe |
Are you excited? Nervous?
Both. I haven't seen him
all summer.
Which is why nerves
are acceptable,
but we agreed, Betty...
It's time.
You like him, he likes you.
Well, then why, Kevin,
hasn't he ever said
or done anything?
Because Archie's swell,
but like most
millennial straight guys,
he needs to be told
what he wants.
So tell him, finally.
Well, we'll see.
I mean, it depends.
Oh, my God!
What?
Game-changer.
Archie got hot!
He's got abs now.
Six more reasons for you
to take that ginger bull
by the horns tonight.
So, what was the highlight?
Of my internship?
The Toni Morrison
book release party
I organized, by far.
At the end of the night,
Toni Morrison,
who is, as you know,
- my literary hero,
says to me...
- Yes. Yes.
"Don't rush this time, Betty.
"It goes by so fast
at your age.
"One summer
can change everything."
Wow. That's so true.
How was working for your dad?
It was...
Pouring concrete,
every day, all day long.
To pass time,
I would start composing
these poems, in my head.
And at night, I'd go home,
I'd write them down...
You don't even
like reading poetry.
They weren't poems,
they were song lyrics.
And working on them
made me feel like...
What, Archie?
It made me feel like
I'd finally broken through
to something real.
About my life
and what I should be trying
to do with it.
Music.
Starting this year, tomorrow.
Amazing.
Will you ask Ms. Grundy
to tutor you?
- I'm not sure, maybe.
- What about football?
- Can you do both?
- I'll try out, at least.
- Well, have you told your dad?
- No.
Until I've got things
more figured out,
you're the only person
I'm telling, okay?
Well, I'd love to hear
them sometime.
Your songs.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
Yeah, I'm finishing
a couple of demos tonight.
Great. Also...
I've been thinking
about us, Archie,
and our friendship,
and how it's time we...
I called in an order,
for Lodge?
Two burgers,
yeah, almost ready,
but you gotta wait.
- Hi.
- Hey.
How are the onion rings here?
So good.
Can we get some onion rings,
too, please?
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
My mom and I
just moved here, so...
- From where?
- New York.
Wow.
Do you guys go to Riverdale?
- We do. Both of us. Together.
- We're sophomores.
Me too.
- I'm filled with dread.
- Why is that?
Are you familiar with the
works of Truman Capote?
I'm Breakfast at Tiffany's,
but this place is strictly In Cold Blood.
Veronica Lodge.
Archie Andrews.
Uh, this is Betty Cooper.
Wait, are you...
Supposed to give you
your tour tomorrow? Yes.
I'm your peer mentor.
Do you want to join us?
Hey, maybe we can
un-fill you with dread.
My mom's waiting for me.
But, to be continued.
Yeah.
- What were you saying?
- Nothing.
Hey, Dad. First day of school
and I'm already late.
Hey, Vegas.
Hey, you, uh,
you stopping by
the site later?
Dad, it's my first day.
Oh, we got to get you going
in the office,
so next summer
you're not on the crew.
Well, I can't.
I've got football tryouts.
Or is that not okay?
No, it's, uh...
It's okay. Good luck.
Hmm.
Betty.
This coming year
is critical for colleges.
Grades are important,
extracurriculars, athletics.
Maintaining
a decent character
is hugely important,
they do look at that.
Mom, I'm a sophomore.
You've accomplished so much,
I don't want anything
jeopardizing that.
I mean, just think
of your poor sister.
She was such a shining star
before she let
that Blossom boy ruin her.
Mom, I'm not Polly.
You missed curfew last night.
By seven minutes.
I was with Archie,
who has red hair, yes,
but is nothing
like Jason Blossom.
Oh, but sweetie, all boys
are like Jason Blossom.
I love you so much,
Elizabeth.
I just need you
to be smart, okay?
And stay...
Focused.
I refilled your Adderall.
Seems you forgot
to pick up your prescription.
Bro, you are ready
for football.
I'm not kidding you, dude.
You got ripped.
Dude, you're a beast.
Look at this arm, it's diesel!
How much are you benching,
like 220? 225?
You got to give me
some tips, man.
Romanian deadlifts, right?
Taking some T?
Ginseng?
Maca root?
Tribulus terrestris?
It's from working
construction, Reg.
Oh, yeah, yeah, that's right.
Yo, Moose.
- Look who grew up
over the summer.
Hey!
Yo,
be honest with me.
You work on any houses?
Any private homes?
Yeah, a couple.
Did you tap some cougar ass
this summer?
You know what,
I think that's more a fantasy
from your wank-bank, Reggie.
- I'll catch you guys soon.
- Peace out, brother.
- Totally did it, bro.
- He totally did it.
So, I usually start off
my tours
with a little history
and context.
Riverdale High first opened
its doors in 1941 and...
And hasn't been redecorated
since, apparently.
Honestly, I feel
like I'm wandering
through the lost epilogue
of Our Town.
Uh-huh.
So what's the social scene
like here? Any night clubs?
A strip club
called the Ho Zone
and a tragic gay bar
called Innuendo.
Friday nights, football games
and then tailgate parties
at the Mallmart parking lot.
Saturday night is movie night,
regardless of what's playing
at the Bijou,
and you better
get there early,
because we don't have
reserved seating in Riverdale.
And Sunday nights...
Thank God for HBO.
Veronica Lodge, Kevin Keller.
- Veronica's new here.
Kevin is...
- ...gay, thank God.
Let's be best friends.
Is it true what they say
about your dad?
That he's the devil incarnate?
I stand by my father.
Does everyone here know?
Wonderful. Ten minutes in
and I'm already
the Blue Jasmine
of Riverdale High.
What?
Mm-mm.
Excuse me,
this is a closed rehearsal.
I'm sorry, I...
Josie, right?
I was hoping
I could talk to you
about some songs that I wrote?
Let me just
stop you right there.
You're staring
at our pussycat ears,
which is rude,
but let me break it,
and them, down for you.
The Pussycats
are building a brand,
creating a signature look,
okay? We're telling a story.
Last year, we won
Rockland County's
Battle of the Bands.
That we did.
This year, we'd like to build
on that success,
continue telling our story
with songs we write.
I get that. It's just...
Read my glossed lips,
Justin Gingerlake.
Not...
Gonna...
Happen.
Oh, and of course there's
the Back-to-School
- semiformal dance
this weekend.
- Oh!
There's the hottie
we were with last night.
The red-headed Ansel Elgort.
Is he your boyfriend?
- No, he's straight.
- No, we're just friends.
In that case,
mind putting in a word?
I've tried every flavor of boy
but orange.
Actually, to clarify...
Betty and Archie
aren't dating,
but they are endgame.
You should ask him
to the semiformal then.
She should, but I heard
it might be getting canceled.
Because of what happened
to Jason.
They're gonna tell us
at the assembly.
Who's Jason
and what happened to him?
Thank you
for that moment of silence.
Many of you were lucky enough
to have known
my brother personally.
Each and every one of you
meant the world to Jason.
I loved my brother.
He was and always will be
my soulmate.
So I speak with the confidence
only a twin could have...
Jason wouldn't want us
to spend the year mourning.
Jason would want us
to move on with our lives.
Which is why I've asked
the School Board
not to cancel
the Back-to-School semiformal.
But rather, to let us use it
as a way
to heal, collectively,
and celebrate my brother's
too, too short life
on this mortal coil.
Thank you all.
- Ms. Grundy? Hey.
- Archie.
What are you doing
walking in this heat?
Um... Building character?
Do you want a ride?
Ms. Grundy. Ms. Grundy.
Geraldine.
What can I do for you,
Mr. Andrews?
Can we talk,
Ms. Grundy, please?
It depends. About what?
Music.
You're the music teacher.
Can we talk about music?
Of course.
Make an appointment.
During my office hours,
my official office hours.
Hermione Lodge.
Well, my day just got
a lot more interesting.
Hello, Fred.
How are you?
Surprised.
Can I get you anything?
Would you like a water?
A job.
I saw on your website
that you are looking
for a seasonal hire,
someone to help
with the books?
Yeah, my guy's
on paternity leave.
You know, I think
my daughter's going to school
with your son,
isn't that funny?
We'll have to tell them
that we knew each other,
that we even dated,
for a little while...
- Well, at least until I...
- ...chose the rich kid.
And now,
a reversal of fortune.
How's Mary doing?
She's in Chicago.
We split up. We're civil.
How about you?
How are you
holding up? Really?
I have a little money saved.
I was praying that someone
in Riverdale,
maybe an old friend,
would be willing to give me
the benefit of the doubt.
If it were up to me.
Isn't it up to you?
It's your company.
Well, I have clients.
I can't very well
have Hermione Lodge,
the wife of Hiram Lodge,
on trial for fraud
and embezzlement,
balancing my books.
Can I?
No.
I suppose you can't.
Can I join?
Yeah.
What are we doing?
Listening to one
of Archie's songs.
I thought we were going
to have to pretend
to like it, but it's actually
really good.
Wait, that was you singing?
- Something you wrote?
- It's rough.
No, it's great.
It's incredible, actually,
the little snippet I heard.
Is that your thing? Music?
Are you doing something
with that?
Yeah, that's the plan.
So how's your
first day going? Good?
Not to be
a complete narcissist,
but I thought people
would be more...
Obsessed with you?
Any other year,
you'd be trending number one,
for sure.
This year, though,
it's all about Cheryl
trying to win
the Best Supporting Psycho
Oscar
for her role
as Riverdale High's
bereaved Red Widow.
Hey, I should go.
I got that meeting with Grundy
and then football tryouts, so.
You play football, too?
What don't you do?
Before you ask,
Blue Jasmine, no,
she has not invited him
to the dance yet...
Not yet, and don't
talk about Archie.
Veronica Lodge,
I'd heard whisperings.
I'm Cheryl Blossom, may I sit?
Betty, would you mind?
So, what are you three hens
gossiping about?
Archie's Efron-esque emergence
from the chrysalis of puberty?
Extracurriculars.
Weatherbee wants me
to sign up for a few.
Cheerleading. You must.
I'm senior captain
of the River Vixens.
Is cheerleading still a thing?
Is being the Gay Best Friend
still a thing?
Some people say it's retro,
I say it's eternal and iconic.
At Spence, I sat at the top
of the Elites' pyramid.
I'm in.
Betty, you're trying out, too.
Of course,
anyone's welcome to try out,
but Betty's already
got so much
on her plate right now
and being a Vixen
is kind of a full-time thing.
But open to all!
Follow me on Twitter
and I'll do the same.
My handle is @cherylbombshell.
Okay. Go ahead and hate
on cheerleading,
but if Hipster Prince Harry...
I'd love to be a cheerleader.
It would look great
on my college applications.
But last year,
when I tried out,
Cheryl said I was too fat.
"Too season 5 Betty Draper."
It was a great line,
but not at all true.
Well, you're a total
smoke show now.
I mean it.
As hot and as smart
as you are,
you should be the
Queen Bey of this drab hive.
Look, if you want
to be a River Vixen,
I'll help you prep.
I have moves.
Okay. You know what?
Show me your moves.
They're...
Very real,
very personal.
I took your advice
and wrote them down.
Polished them.
But I was wondering maybe
if you could help me...
With what, Archie?
You went to Juilliard,
Ms. Grundy.
There is no one else
in Riverdale
I can take lessons from.
Believe me, I've looked.
Well, I don't think
that's a good idea.
I don't think we should
be alone together.
If this is you trying
to restart something
that never should've
started in the first...
No, it's not.
It is about the music.
But it's also...
Come on,
I need to be able
to talk about what happened
with someone.
We heard what we heard
and afterwards,
we didn't do anything.
We didn't say anything.
We heard fireworks.
Who's lighting fireworks
at 6:00 in the morning?
How would we explain
why we were together
at Sweetwater River
at 6:00 a.m.
on the Fourth of July?
And you're right.
We didn't say anything.
We're both going to have to
live with that choice.
Do you understand?
I think you should
pursue your music,
but not with me.
We're dynamite!
We'll take you down,
and fight the fight!
Whoo! Go, Bulldogs!
Hmm.
Ladies, where's the heat?
Where's the sizzle?
Well, you haven't seen
our big finish yet.
Don't freak out.
Just trust me.
Check your
sell-by date, ladies,
faux lesbian kissing
hasn't been taboo since 1994.
So let's see if you do better
with the interview portion
of our audition.
Betty,
how's your sister doing?
Um, Polly's fine,
thanks for asking.
Veronica, has Betty told you
about her sister yet?
- Uh, no.
- Go ahead, Betty.
Tell Veronica
about your sister
and my dear brother.
Polly and Jason dated.
I wouldn't say "dated".
- It didn't end well.
- In fact,
Jason's probably why
your sister had
a nervous breakdown
and now lives in a group home,
isn't it?
That's what my parents think.
What do you have to say
about that, Betty?
Go ahead, the floor is yours.
Whatever you've been dying
to spew about Jason
and how he treated Polly,
unleash it.
Destroy me. Tear me a new one.
Rip me to shreds.
Annihilate me.
I just...
Finally.
I just wanted
to say I'm sorry
about what happened to Jason.
I can't even imagine
what you and your family
must be going through.
Right.
Veronica,
welcome to the River Vixens.
Betty, better luck next time.
Wait, what? Why?
Because you couldn't bully
Betty into being a bitch?
I need girls with fire
on my squad.
I know what you need, Cheryl,
because I know who you are.
You would rather
people fear
than like you,
so you traffic
in terror and intimidation.
You're rich, so you've never
been held accountable,
but I'm living proof.
That certainty,
that entitlement
you wear on your head
like a crown?
It won't last.
Eventually, there will be
a reckoning.
Or...
Maybe that reckoning
is now.
And maybe, that reckoning...
Is me.
Betty and I come
as a matching set.
You want one,
you take us both.
You wanted fire?
Sorry, Cherylbombshell,
my specialty's ice.
Go, get around him.
Get around him.
Let's move.
Andrews!
There we go. Looking good.
- What's up, Coach?
- Here.
- This is Jason's number.
- It's yours now.
Usually, sophomores,
they only play JV.
This year, we've got
an open spot in varsity.
From what you've
been showing us,
well, I want you to fill it.
Varsity's got
longer practices.
More away games.
Yeah, bigger commitment, yeah.
Well, I need to think
about it, Coach. I...
Oh, what, you got
something better to do?
My dad's company.
It's our family business,
and he's sort of counting
on me to help out
after school, on weekends...
Hold up, Jackson,
hold the ball.
You know what,
why don't you sleep on it.
Let's go. Bring it in, guys.
Come on.
Perfect.
Very Betty Draper, season 1.
Veronica.
Why did...
Why did you defend me?
I know the crowd
you ran with
in New York.
Why are you being so... Nice?
When my father got arrested,
it was the worst thing ever.
All these trolls
started writing
horrible things about us.
We'd get letters and e-mails
saying that
my dad was a thief,
my mom
was a clueless socialite,
and that I was
the spoiled rich-bitch
ice princess.
And what hurt the most
about it was...
The things the trolls
were writing were true.
I was like Cheryl.
I was worse than Cheryl.
So, when my mom said
we were moving to Riverdale,
I made a pact with myself
to use this
as an opportunity
to become
maybe, hopefully,
a better version of myself.
That's a lot of pressure.
When Polly and Jason
got together...
It meant everything to her
and nothing to him,
and...
And things got super
intense and weird and toxic
and my mom turned on Polly.
Said Polly wasn't
her daughter anymore,
said all these
awful things to her.
Jason hurt Polly,
but it's my mom who broke her.
Archie.
- You're so doing this.
- What?
Slaying your dragons,
Betty Cooper, one by one.
- Hi, Teen Outlander.
- Hey.
Nice outfits.
Betty here has something
she wants to ask you
about the
Back-to-School dance.
Go on, Betty, ask.
I was wondering
if you wanted
to come
with both of us.
- Huh?
- What?
It's your first dance
at Riverdale.
You should have
someone to go with,
even if it's just a friend.
I mean, I'd love to.
I'm not really in the
headspace for a dance.
Oh. That's okay.
Totally unacceptable,
Archiekins.
We need an escort.
Take a break from being
a tortured musical genius
and come spend
a blissful evening
with not one, but two
newly-minted River Vixens.
We'll text you time and place.
Okay. Yeah, okay.
- Bye.
What is that?
I made the cheerleading squad.
Cheryl Blossom's
cheerleading squad?
After what Jason did to Polly?
No, I'm sorry.
I won't allow it.
Take that off right now.
- No.
- What did you say to me?
I do everything for everyone.
Everything to be perfect.
The perfect daughter,
the perfect sister,
the perfect student...
Can't I do this one thing
just for me?
- Wait.
- Get out of my way.
- Where are you going?
- To buy a dress.
Because guess what?
I'm also gong to the dance
with Archie.
And Veronica.
Wait. Hermione Lodge's
daughter?
She's actually really nice.
And trying
to be a good person.
You think so?
You think she's going to be
your friend?
Let me tell you something.
Girls like Cheryl
and Veronica Lodge,
they don't like girls like us.
I don't want to hear it, Mom.
It's happening. I'm going.
Thank you, Smithers.
As always, you're a godsend.
Happy to help, Ms. Hermione.
Unlike the rest of Riverdale.
- Hmm.
- What's that?
Oh. Um...
A spot of good news.
The car service
found and dropped off
your missing bag.
Missing bag?
Oh, Hiram...
What have you done?
I, um... I got a call
from your coach today.
He's under the impression
that you can't play
varsity football
because I'm making you
work for me.
Which is odd,
because you made it
seem like
you couldn't work for me
because you were
playing football.
So my first question is...
Who are you lying to?
Me or your coach?
Neither.
Both.
Dad...
I want to study music,
I want to write music.
Football takes you to college.
College takes you
to business school.
- Business school...
- Takes me back here.
To work for you in Riverdale.
Not for me, with me.
And eventually
for yourself, son.
The company would be yours.
No disrespect, Dad,
but I don't want it.
Three months ago, you did.
What happened?
I've changed.
Everything's changed.
This summer...
This summer what?
That's it?
We don't talk anymore?
Dad.
I would never force you
to play football.
I don't care
if you play football.
And you don't have to work
with me or for me, ever again.
But some advice, man-to-man?
These decisions
that you're making now, son,
they have consequences.
They go on to form who you are
and who you'll become.
Whatever you decide,
be confident enough in it
that you don't have to lie.
Well, it's not the Met Ball.
Hey. When do you have
to let Coach Clayton
- know about football?
- This weekend.
Guys, can't we just
liberate ourselves
from the tired dichotomy
of jock/artist?
Can't we, in this post
James Franco world,
be all things at once?
I've been working
on it, Veronica.
Work faster.
I'm getting punch.
You got this.
It's about following
your heart, right?
What does your heart say?
Music or football?
Betty, will you give me
one minute?
And I promise,
when I get back,
I'll be a much
better date, okay?
I have a plan.
Betty, you will not believe
who just propositioned me
in the bathroom.
Give you a hint...
His name may be Moose,
but I'd describe
a certain appendage of his
as horse-like.
Don't panic,
I'm not stalking you.
Archie, didn't we
have a deal?
No, Geraldine,
we have a secret,
Multiple secrets, actually.
And maybe we could've
done something
to help Jason that morning,
or maybe we couldn't have.
And I won't tell
anyone anything,
but you need to help me.
This summer, the only thing
that kept me sane
was writing these songs.
So here's my
not-so-indecent proposal.
I want to do
an independent study with you,
as many mornings a week
as you can spare, and I swear
that's all it'll be.
And I won't tell anyone
about July Fourth, ever.
Deal?
Monday, Wednesday,
Friday, 7:30 a.m.,
before first period.
I'll set it up
and see about getting
you credit.
Good evening, friends.
Are you all having
a good time?
As honorary chairperson
and de facto queen
of tonight's semiformal,
it is my great pleasure
to introduce this evening's
main entertainment.
To know them
is to be obsessed with them.
Though they usually perform
their own material,
tonight, they're making
an exception
and debuting a cover
of the song my parents claim
they were listening to
the night Jason and I
were conceived.
This one's for you, JJ.
- Sorry about that.
- I give you
Josie and the Pussycats.
- Wanna dance?
- Yeah.
Did that go okay?
Yeah, yes. I'll study
with Ms. Grundy
before school,
football practice
after school,
and work with my dad
on the weekends.
It's going to be nuts.
So long as you don't give up
your passion.
Um...
Now that I'm a River Vixen
and you're gonna be
on varsity football,
I have this fantasy of us
as a power couple...
Or maybe even just
a couple.
Betty...
Is that so impossible
to imagine?
Make sure those two
turtledoves
come to my after-party.
Veronica too.
I'm in the mood
for chaos.
It's game time at
Chez Blossom, kiddies.
We're going
old-school tonight.
Seven Minutes in Heaven.
Who wants to tryst
in the Closet of Love first?
My vote is "A" for Archie.
Anyone care to second it?
- Wait, actually...
- Yes, Andrews! Yes.
All right. Gather round, kids.
Let's see who's riding
the ginger stallion tonight.
Oh, no way!
It's clearly pointing to...
The new girl.
This should be fun.
Um... I'm not doing this.
That's up to you.
But, if you don't,
house rules decree
the hostess
gets to take your turn.
I know her brother died
and everything,
but...
Cheryl Blossom
truly is the antichrist.
So, uh, do you miss New York?
It's been less than a week.
But... Yes.
Six minutes, twenty seconds.
Okay. Your turn.
Ask me a deep,
probing question
to kill time.
It looked like you and Betty
were having fun at the dance.
Definitely. We've been
friends forever.
- My turn.
- I didn't ask my question yet.
Is that all it is?
Just friends?
We're not just friends,
we're best friends.
My turn. Did you have
a boyfriend in New York?
No.
My turn.
Could it ever possibly
become something more?
Are you asking for Betty
or for yourself?
For Betty, and you didn't
answer my question.
I have never felt...
Whatever it is
I'm supposed to feel
with Betty.
Have you felt it, though?
With anyone?
Yeah.
This summer.
- Have you?
- Maybe once.
You're a little more dangerous
than you look, aren't you?
All boy-next-door-ish?
You have no idea.
Your turn.
Ask me a question, Archie.
Ask me anything you want.
We shouldn't do this.
We definitely shouldn't
do this.
Nailed it.
Yes.
Where's Betty?
She spiraled and fled.
Between us, she's a lot more
high-strung than she looks.
You shady bitch.
Crap. Betty's cell is off.
- I'm getting an Uber.
- Can I come with you?
We should probably
try to find her.
Believe me.
The last thing
Betty wants
is us tracking
her down together.
We messed up.
Hey, you're home early.
How was the dance?
It was fine.
I mean, it's not the Met Ball
or anything...
Tell me about it.
You can cheer me up.
I'm super tired, Mom.
Is everything okay?
Ronnie, what is it?
It was midnight,
when my old friend
Archie Andrews
arrived at the one place
in town that was still open.
He was looking
for the girl next door.
Instead, he found me.
Hey, Pop. Betty hasn't come
in tonight, has she?
Nope.
Just the night hawks
in tonight.
Thanks.
Uh, can I sit, Jughead?
If you want.
- What are you working on?
- My novel.
It's about this summer,
and Jason Blossom.
Seventeen years old
and how will he be remembered?
As captain
of the water polo team?
The Aquaholics?
Considering how he died,
probably not.
No, what I mean is...
Was he doing everything
he was supposed to do,
everything he wanted.
I mean, did he even know
what that was?
Coach Clayton was in here
talking to Pop Tate.
Varsity.
Does that make you, what,
Mr. Popular Football God now?
No.
In fact, I'm kind of terrified
I lost my
best friend tonight.
If you mean Betty,
whatever happened,
just talk to her.
You know,
it'd go a long way.
Would've gone a long way
with me.
I'm not going to ask
what you did
with Veronica at Cheryl's.
But I'm asking you now,
right now,
if you love me, Archie.
Or even like me?
Of course I love you, Betty.
But I can't give you
the answer you want.
Why?
You are so perfect.
I've never been
good enough for you.
I'll never be
And so,
it wasn't one heart
that broke that night.
It was two.
And the night was far
from over.
For the record, I'm not gay.
Obviously not, Moose.
You're on the football team.
But if you were gay,
what would you like to do?
Everything but kiss.
I love a good closet case.
So, let's start with
skinny-dipping
and then see what happens?
Dude, are you okay?
Oh, my God, it's Jason.
He was shot.
By morning,
everyone would be
talking, texting,
and posting about it.
We'd all be feeling it.
That the world around us
had changed,
maybe forever.
That Riverdale wasn't
the same town
as before.
That it was a town
of shadows and secrets now.
On Monday,
the autopsy on Jason's body
would take place.
And on Tuesday,
halfway through fifth period,
the first arrest
would be made.
Subtittle By | SupunWe |