Previously on Riverdale...
This story is about a town,
once wholesome and innocent,
now forever changed
by the mysterious
death of Jason Blossom
on the 4th of July.
- Can we talk, Ms. Grundy?
- About what?
You're the music
teacher, can we talk
about music?
We heard what we heard
and afterwards
we didn't do anything.
How would we explain why
we were together at 6:00 a.m.
on the 4th of July?
Hello, Fred.
- Can I get you anything?
- A job.
I can't very well have
the wife of Hiram Lodge,
on trial for fraud
and embezzlement,
balancing my books.
Betty and Archie
are endgame.
I'm not gonna
ask what you did
with Veronica at Cheryl's.
I'm asking you now, right now,
if you love me, Archie.
I can't give you
the answer you want.
Oh, my God, it's Jason.
He was shot.
I think many of us,
maybe the entire town,
had been hoping against hope
that somehow Jason Blossom
hadn't drowned on July 4th.
That we'd come to school
Monday morning,
and there Jason would be.
Or that we'd see him
and Cheryl in a booth
at Pop's.
But that was before the
undeniable, irrevocable fact
of his bloated,
water-logged body,
a corpse with a bullet hole
in its forehead,
and terrible secrets that
could only be revealed
by the cold, steel blade of
a coroner's autopsy scalpel,
or the telltale beating
of a guilty heart.
Archie, what are
you doing here?
- It wasn't fireworks,
Ms. Grundy.
- You can't be here, Archie.
- On July 4th,
it was a gunshot we heard.
- You can't come to my house.
Probably the shot that
killed Jason Blossom.
We know exactly
what the police know.
That a gun was fired.
That a boy was shot.
We don't know by whom.
We know when it was fired.
That's something
the police still don't know.
They're performing
an autopsy.
We could call
them, anonymously.
This is not a negotiation,
Archie. This is our lives.
If anybody knows
that we were there,
I could lose my job.
You could be expelled.
We could go to jail.
Subtittle By | SupunWe |
All right.
Here you go, Vegas.
Good boy.
Wow.
- Morning, Dad.
- Hey, bud.
Where'd you sneak
off to last night?
You, uh, you heard that?
Son, I've been hearing you
sneak out since you were
eight years old
going to Jughead's tree house.
I couldn't sleep.
Went for a jog to tire
myself out.
Yeah? Got something
on your mind?
- Just all this stuff
with Jason.
- Hmm.
No more midnight runs until
the police catch whoever it
was that shot that poor kid.
I swear to God, this town.
Hey, honey?
We just wanted you to know,
it's gonna be a bit of a
late night for us.
It's going to be
a lot of late nights for us.
I mean, an accidental
drowning, who cares?
But the sociopathic son
of the wealthiest family
in town, murdered?
That's a national obsession
waiting to happen.
He's barely
in his grave, Alice.
Can you warm up the car, Hal?
I'll be right down.
Betty, you know what
I love most about you?
It's that you always want to
see the good in people.
Even people
like Cheryl Blossom
and Veronica Lodge
and Archie Andrews.
But when they
betrayed you this weekend,
you saw
their true colors, didn't you?
I did. I definitely did.
So no backsliding.
No Cheryl. No Veronica and...
No Archie.
Walk me to school?
I needed time to process.
To separate what my mom
wants from what I want...
I think I want.
Which is?
My mom says I should
never speak to you again.
But I...
Even though you don't
like me like that,
I still want us to be
friends... Best friends.
You do?
Yeah.
I mean, that's great, Betty.
Me, too.
I'd be lying if
I said that it didn't hurt.
And I'm sorry, Betty,
I didn't do it to be a...
I don't know, I just...
I thought it would be
better in the long run.
And it will be.
Oh, and don't tell my mom
that we're friends again.
Hi.
Do you think I can use Jason
Blossom's death as an excuse
to get out of PE?
"Sorry, Coach, I'm just too
depressed and freaked-out
right now to do pull-ups."
Don't joke about
Jason Blossom.
What?
Sardonic humor
is just my way of relating
to the world.
Look, it's the
rich kids from The Goonies.
All right, I'm out.
Watch it, Wednesday Addams.
Now that romance is off
the table, I'll just say it.
Are we 100% sure
that Archie's straight?
Because no straight man
has that body.
Speaking of bodies...
Have you recovered from
finding Jason's?
It was more traumatizing
having to explain to my dad
what I was doing
with Moose at the river.
Yet another perk
of being the sheriff's son.
Oh, my God,
those are gorgeous.
Are those for Betty,
Mrs. Philips?
That's why I called her.
"Dear Betty,
please forgive me, XOXO, V."
Who the hell is "V"?
- Veronica.
The yellow is for friendship.
I also had Magnolia cupcakes
flown in from New York.
Because, as my mom
likes to say,
"There's no wrong the right
cupcake can't fix."
Also I... I've booked us
for hers-and-hers mani-pedis
at Chez Salon.
Blowouts, too.
I am so, so sorry, Betty.
I don't know what happened
to me that night. It was such
a basic bitch move.
It was like I was...
Possessed by...
Madame Satan?
The old Veronica.
And I will never, ever do
anything like that to
you again.
I swear on my mother's pearls.
Just, can you please give me
one more chance?
Okay.
- What?
Really?
Awesome. I'll take it
and you won't regret it.
Okay.
And I'll bring these
to lunch so we can celebrate!
It's the path of least
resistance, Kev.
A week ago, Veronica
and I weren't friends.
Next week, we'll nod
to each other as we pass
in the hall, but that's it.
You know, in two weeks,
she won't even
remember my name.
And in three,
she'll have latched on to
some other girl to destroy.
Good morning,
students. This is your
principal speaking.
There have been many inquiries
about the upcoming pep rally.
So let me state clearly,
it is happening, as scheduled.
Now, on a less felicitous
note, if you could give your
attention to Sheriff Keller.
Most of you already
know the details,
but your classmate
Jason Blossom's body
was found late Saturday night.
So as of the weekend,
Jason's death is now being
treated as a homicide.
It is an open
and ongoing investigation.
And may I interject,
neither I nor my parents
will rest until Jason's
death is avenged,
and his cold-hearted killer
is walking the green mile
to sit in Old Sparky and fry.
I, for one,
have my suspicions.
Hashtag Riverdale strong.
If you know anything
that could help us find
and apprehend Jason's killer,
or anything about what
happened to him on July 4th,
I strongly urge you to
come forward immediately.
You can speak with me
or Principal Weatherbee.
A death like this
wounds us all.
Let's not let Jason down.
Archie.
Weirdest thing.
This summer, we were
supposed to go on a road trip
over July 4th weekend...
Which you bailed on
at the last minute.
Is there something
you wanna tell me, pal?
We were wondering, Cheryl.
Back in July, you told
the po-po that Jason drowned.
Yet, we come to find out
that Jason didn't drown.
He was shot. That's
slightly suspicious, no?
Are you living mannequins
suggesting I had something
to do with my brother's death?
We're just curious. What do
the police think happened?
I'll tell you what I told
them, which is that Jason
did fall into the water.
We both did.
I made it to the shore.
He didn't.
Maybe he made it to the other
side of the river and someone
shot him there. Who knows?
Seats, everyone. Pair off,
gloves on, scalpels up.
Can I be with Cheryl?
And I wanna be with Betty.
Oh, uh, I was thinking
I'd partner with Kevin.
Actually, uh,
Keller's with me.
We, like, talked.
Oh, God.
- Once again,
fate throws us together.
- Hmm.
So... Saturday night.
Listen, Moose,
you're hot. Yes.
My type? Definitely.
But you've got more
demons than The Exorcist.
We're all on the spectrum,
but my gay-o-meter
says you should stick with
what you know best... Girls.
Cheryl, we haven't talked
since the summer.
I just want to say, I'm really
sorry about your brother.
Jason was the best.
If I can do anything to help.
That's sweet, Archie,
but unless you were
at Sweetwater River
and know who shot Jason...
Do, uh, do you know if
the police have any leads?
What? No, you ghoul. But it's
only a matter of time.
And my twintuition
is telling me it's someone
we all know.
Right. Well,
I'm not great at science,
but I can take point on this
if it's too weird for you.
Weird, why?
Oh, you mean because
my brother is being
dissected with a blade,
just like this one, possibly
at this very moment?
Don't worry, I'm fine.
In fact, I'm amazing.
Every corpse has
as tale to tell.
Step closer to the body.
There are several morbid
details you should find
relevant to your article.
What details, Dr. Curdle?
What sticks out to you?
The marbling of the veins.
Signs of scavenger activity.
Ligature marks on both wrists.
And a hint
of cryo-necrotic preservation.
Small bills, right?
So, what did Moose want?
Oh, my God,
I don't even think he knows.
I mean, I am devastatingly
handsome in that classic,
pre-accident Montgomery Clift
kind of way,
and sexuality is fluid,
but can someone named
Moose actually be that fluid?
Okay, well, I ship it.
Well, of course you would.
You're a big city
girl with loose morals.
I just meant that Moose has
an official girlfriend, Midge.
Anyway, it's terrible to say,
but part of me wishes he would
just stay in the darn closet.
Obviously, I didn't
mean literal closet.
Archie!
Any new material
you wanna try out on
a very forgiving audience?
I...
Please?
Would you?
I'd love to hear it.
I'm still working
on the lyrics, so...
Okay.
♪ Come on, turn the radio on
♪ And, honey
we'll dance, dance, dance
♪ For the rest of the night
♪ I'm not ready to go ♪
Betty?
You okay?
I'm supposed to say, "Yes."
That's what the nice girl
always says, but...
No, I'm not.
I want to be.
I thought I could be.
But it's too much, too fast.
- Archie...
- Betty.
Betty, wait.
- Betty, wait. Come on.
Listen to me.
- No.
No, when... When I think,
Archie, of where I feel safest
and most myself,
- I think of us,
in a booth, at Pop's...
- Me, too.
But that's not true anymore.
I thought I could pretend this
weekend didn't happen, but...
"I can't give you
the answer you want."
That's what you said to me.
And that's how I feel
right now, I'm sorry.
Betty.
Mr. Andrews.
If we could have
a word in private.
You're in a very good place
right now, Mr. Andrews.
Varsity football,
AP music tutorials.
This morning, in the hallway,
you wouldn't meet my eyes.
Why?
I was distracted.
I wasn't feeling well.
Archie...
If there's something you want
to get off your chest,
perhaps about Jason,
now would be the time.
Weatherbee just asked me if
I knew anything about Jason.
And?
What did you say?
Nothing. That I didn't.
But he said that if I did,
I shouldn't be scared,
and he'd make sure I was okay.
Of course he would,
you're his student.
Is this...
How you feel about me?
Is it real?
Because if it's not,
then I don't know
what I'm protecting.
It is.
It is real.
Maybe it's not right,
but it's real.
Which is why...
We... You...
Can't go to Weatherbee.
If you do that,
we will never see each
other again.
Archie,
I'm putting myself in
your hands.
♪ L-E-T-S G-o
♪ Let's go, let's go
♪ Go and get it, get it
Stand down, Vixens.
And listen up.
The weather's
predicting a downpour
the night of the rally,
but already, you're raining
on my parade.
With Jason so present in our
collective consciousness,
all eyes will be on me.
Will this beautiful, exotic,
hothouse flower
drown under the
town's scrutiny,
or be swamped by her emotions?
The answer, ladies,
is "no" and "no."
That said, I need star power.
I need the Pussycats.
Stay loose and limber, ladies,
while I make a call.
After this practice, I'll
totally need a pedicure. You?
I'll have homework.
I know everyone
grieves differently,
but Cheryl's hosting
a pep rally to cope
with her loss.
That's either brilliant,
or psychotic, or both.
Yeah, well, at least Cheryl's
not putting on an act.
Pretending she's a butterfly
when really she's a wasp.
For the record,
the only reason I went
into that closet with Archie
was so that Cheryl wouldn't.
- Oh, so you did
it to protect me?
- Damn straight.
Okay, so nothing happened
between you and Archie
in the closet, then?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
You know, Archie and I were
fine before you got here.
If by, fine,
you mean he was oblivious
and you were pining after him
in quiet desperation.
We were friends, at least.
You were walking on emotional
eggshells around him,
scared to tell him the truth.
Okay, you don't
know me, Veronica.
It is not my fault he
doesn't like you.
If that's what
you're thinking.
It's not anyone's fault.
It's not even stupid Archie's.
It's just how it is.
Most of the time
the people we like
don't like us back.
Romeo and Juliet are
the exception, not the rule.
Look...
Never speak to me again.
If that's what you want,
I'll accept that.
But what, exactly,
did Archie do wrong?
- Are you seriously
taking his side?
- No, I'm not taking any...
And this is your way of trying
to be friends with me again?
The Pussycats are in.
Oh, sorry, ladies,
am I interrupting?
- As a matter of fact...
- No, you're not.
Actually, I was about
to come and find you, Cheryl.
I have a gift certificate for
hers-and-hers mani-pedis
and blowouts at Chez Salon.
- Do you want to come with me?
- Don't do this.
Butt out, closet monster.
You have forfeited
your right to take
the high and mighty road.
As pour moi, Betty,
but of course.
I never say no to a pedi.
And I was just about to
suggest the same thing.
Can I steal her for a second?
You're doing great, Mom.
Better than me this week.
Yeah, we're surviving,
Ronnie, by our wits,
because that's what
we Lodge women do.
If Dad could see us now.
He'd say you look stunning
in that new uniform.
I'm going for this
Joan Crawford, Mildred Pierce
thing. Is it working?
Definitely.
Hi.
And who might this
heartbreaker be?
I'm picking up an order
for Andrews.
Oh, you're Fred's son?
You're as handsome
as your father was.
I'll see you
at home, Mom.
Uh, wait. I'm sure Archie
would happily escort you.
Is, uh, Betty still
mad at you?
We're back to no texting.
What about you?
I'm back to being the shallow,
toxic, rich bitch who ruins
everything in her path.
Which is unfortunate,
because even though
I only just met Betty,
it really felt like
we were meant
to be best friends.
Like... Like it was
our destiny, and now...
It's like there was
this train that was heading
to the rest of my life
and I just missed it.
Betty and I have been
next-door neighbors
since we were four.
We've always gone
to the same school,
been in the same class.
I remember in
the second grade,
I was having trouble reading,
and my teacher, Mrs. Gribrock,
told my mom and dad that
I should stay back a year,
to get caught up.
Betty was so against us
not being in the same grade
that she took it upon herself
to tutor me every single day.
- In the second grade?
- Yeah.
Anyway, when I passed,
thanks to Betty,
I kissed her and I asked
her to marry me.
She was like,
"Oh, little Archie,
we're too young."
"Ask me when we're 18
and I'll say yes."
Wow.
I hate that I hurt her.
Give her time, Archie.
That's all you can do.
And don't despair.
I don't think your story
with Betty is over.
Your room's so sweet.
It's too pink.
It doesn't feel right anymore.
No, I like how girly it is.
Mine is, too.
You should come over
and see it sometime.
But, just you, not Veronica.
I mean, she must be evil
incarnate if even you won't
have her as a friend.
And on the subject
of being friends,
Betty, I'm sorry I've been
such a witchy-witch to you.
After Polly and Jason's
epic demise
I was angry...
At everyone.
But I took it out on you
which was super unfair.
Especially since,
in a way, it's kinda like
we both lost siblings.
How, uh, how is Polly?
Is she still in that
group home?
Do you think she knows
what happened to Jason,
that he was murdered?
I...
I'm not sure.
What do you think
went down between them?
I don't know...
What do your parents say?
About Jason and Polly?
Not a lot.
Same.
I keep thinking that maybe
Jason said something to her
or she said something to him.
I mean, didn't they have
a big fight this summer, or...
Why are you asking me
so many questions about Polly?
Cheryl?
Because, you dumb cow,
someone shot my brother
and I think it was your crazy,
tweaked-out sister.
Get out of my house.
Not until you tell me...
Cheryl, get the hell out of my
house before I kill you.
Jug. What's up?
What's up is
I saw you, Archie.
In the music room.
With Ms. Grundy.
Keep your voice down,
my dad's inside.
I'm trying to help you, dude.
I'm trying to be
your friend here.
Even though we're not anymore.
How long?
You and Grundy?
Since the summer.
I like her.
So I'm guessing
she's the reason you've been
acting weird since summer?
One of them.
"One of them." There's more?
We were at
Sweetwater River on July 4th.
We heard a gunshot.
The gunshot.
- Dude, you have
to tell somebody.
- I can't.
Neither can you. If people
find out about Grundy...
A kid is dead, Archie!
And you're worried about
some... Some cougar?
Don't call her that.
Okay, she's not like that,
she cares about me.
Stab in the dark.
I'm guessing she
cares more about herself.
She's the one
who's telling you
not to say anything, right?
Look, I saw you guys.
She's messing with you, man.
And she's messing
with your mind...
What the hell do you
know about it, Jughead?
Or about me, even?
Nothing.
But I used to know
this guy once.
Archie Andrews.
He wasn't perfect but...
He always tried to do
the right thing, at least.
Jug.
If you tell anyone
about this...
What?
What are you gonna do?
Hey, Jug. Coming in?
We got take-out from Pop's.
He was just leaving.
A little sage,
to banish the evil spirits.
Mom.
I'm not joking, Betty.
That family is pure evil.
I'm wondering if the Blossoms
didn't kill Jason themselves.
Sacrificed him to some dark
pagan god that they worship in
that insane mansion of theirs.
Mom, does Polly know?
About Jason?
I told her.
But half the time, your sister
doesn't even know
what day it is.
Mom, why were you so against
them being together?
Many reasons.
That family. Everything
they touch, it rots.
Mom, I was thinking...
Maybe it's time I go
visit Polly.
I am so proud of how you
stood up to that dragoness,
but honestly, Betty,
why was Cheryl over here
in the first place?
And who else is gonna
come waltzing in?
Veronica? Archie?
How many times are you
gonna let them hurt you?
Until I learn my lesson, Mom.
You were right.
And what you said
about Archie.
Sometimes it's hard
to admit things to yourself.
My mother is crazy.
I'm afraid I'll never
see my sister again.
The boy I like doesn't
like me back.
He may not be crushing on you,
but he does love you.
And he's legit
miserable without you,
if it's any consolation.
My mom says
sometimes a friend
is better than a boyfriend.
Maybe this is one
of those times.
And Sheriff Keller's grilling
me, Mantle the Magnificent.
'Cause I'd want Blossom dead.
When he was, like, the only
good quarterback we had.
And speaking of offensive
tight-ends, I should've sent
the cops to you, Moose.
Because here's
another unsolved mystery.
What exactly were you
and Kevin doing
at the river, huh?
Or does being with
the sheriff's son give you
a free pass? Keller?
Reggie's just being
a blowhard, Kev.
I don't care what he says.
I mean, let's think about it.
If a kid at Riverdale
killed Jason,
it's not gonna
be a jock, right?
Now let's be honest.
Isn't it always some
spooky, scrawny,
pathetic Internet troll,
too busy writing
his manifestos to get laid?
Some smug, moody,
serial killer fanboy freak,
like Jughead?
What was it like,
Suicide Squad?
When you shot Jason?
You didn't do stuff
to the body, did you?
Like... After?
It's called necrophilia,
Reggie, can you spell it?
Come here, you little...
Hey shut the hell up, Reggie.
Boys.
What do you care, Andrews?
Nothing, just leave him alone.
Holy crap.
Did you and Donnie Darko
kill him together?
Was it some sort of pervy,
blood brother thing?
♪ No she don't mess around
Ooh.
I hate to ask this,
but did you get that
in a fight with Jughead?
Nah. No, it was with Reggie.
It's a long story.
Jughead and I, we were
disagreeing about a girl.
Hmm.
- Because there's this girl.
- There usually is.
But it's not about me
and Jughead, it's about
me and this girl.
I think we should
do something.
And it's the right thing, Dad.
But the girl says that if we
do or if I do this thing,
it'll ruin what we have.
That doesn't make
any sense, does it?
You know,
this is the most honest talk
we've had in a while.
And I'm glad that you want
to do the right thing.
I can see that.
Even under the shiner.
Archie, if you know
it's the right thing to do,
even though it's tough,
even though it might...
It might cost you.
You gotta do it.
I'm gonna come clean
with Weatherbee and Keller.
I was there.
I heard the gunshot and
I have to own that.
- Archie, slow down.
- I'm gonna do it tomorrow.
If you wanna come with me,
then we can figure that out.
If not, I'll respect that
and I'll do everything I can
to keep you out of it.
I'm sorry, Ms. Grundy,
but I have to.
Girl trouble? You?
Grundy and me.
We're telling Weatherbee.
At least, I am.
And also, I didn't mean
all that crap I said to you.
I'm sorry.
It's cool.
We're not gonna hug in front
of this whole town.
So why don't we both
just do that bro thing
where we nod like douches
and mutually
suppress our emotions?
Yeah, but as friends, right?
To be discussed,
over many burgers,
and many days.
Oh, my God, Arch. Your eye.
Now to kickoff this pep rally,
I'd like to hand it over
to our very own Mayor McCoy.
Thank you,
Principal Weatherbee.
It is heartening to see
so many of you here,
even in weather like this.
But a lack of heart
and school spirit has never
been the Riverdale way.
Tonight's pep rally
isn't like any other
we've had in the past.
And we shouldn't
pretend that it is.
Which is why I would like
to dedicate this evening
to the memory of
one of our brightest.
Jason Blossom.
We're with him tonight.
Now please, join me
in welcoming to the field
our very own River Vixens,
and their special
guest stars, my daughter,
Josie and her Pussycats!
♪ Hey, shawty
You're my candy girl
The kind with the swirls
♪ Oh, so good
Baby out of this world
♪ Looks so sweet
Fell in love with your curves
♪ Every time you speak
Conversation like, sir
♪ S-U-G-A-R
You ain't her
♪ Oh, honey, honey
Put money on that girl
♪ Let's keep it in her circle
You everything I deserve
♪ Baby wants her sugar
I'm ready to get served
♪ Sugar
♪ Oh, honey, honey
♪ You are my candy girl
♪ And you got me wanting you
♪ Ooh
♪ I saw this girl
I wanna know her name
♪ She's got this body
It's driving me insane
♪ 'Cause I need a candy, girl
♪ Her kisses rock my world
♪ More legs, brown eyes
Ain't nobody like a fancy girl
♪ Sugar
♪ Oh, honey, honey
♪ You are my candy girl
♪ And you got me wanting you ♪
All right, you all ready?
Let's make some noise!
Put your hands together
for the Riverdale Bulldogs!
Cheryl?
Cheryl, what is it?
What happened?
Jason.
He's gone...
I know. I know he is.
No, you don't.
You don't understand.
He was supposed to come back.
I'm alone.
You're not alone. It's okay.
Hey.
I saw you and Cheryl.
Not many girls
would've done what you did.
Full disclosure.
I've had my share
of emotional breakdowns.
If you're not doing anything,
do you wanna go get
a milkshake at Pop's?
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Betty, I'd love that.
Here you go.
One double chocolate
and one old-fashioned vanilla.
- Thank you.
Betty...
Can we make a vow?
Sure.
That no matter what,
no boy will ever come
between us again.
Deal?
Deal.
Do you guys want to join us?
Yes, but only
if you're treating.
- Veronica Lodge.
- Jughead Jones, the third.
Jughead Jones, the third.
To someone on the
outside, peering in,
it would've looked like
there were four people
in that booth.
But I was there,
and I can tell you.
Really, there were only three.
A blonde girl,
a raven-haired girl,
and the luckiest red-headed
boy in the universe.
For one shining moment,
we were just kids.
Those bright neon lights
of Pop's keeping
the darkness at bay.
Giving way,
as all nights must,
to a morning of reckonings.
♪ Got so much to lose
♪ Got so much to prove
♪ God, don't let me lose
My mind
We're reviewing
new systems of human
biology starting with...
♪ My sweet love,
Won't you pull me through
♪ Everywhere I look
I catch a glimpse of you
♪ I said it was love
And I did it for love
♪ I did it for you
You're here for me,
aren't you?
Because of the autopsy?
We don't need
to do this in front of your
classmates, Cheryl.
It's all right,
Principal Weatherbee.
They'll find out soon enough.
Now, that won't be necessary.
Wait, Cheryl, find out what?
That I'm guilty.
As shocking
as those three words were,
they were nothing
compared to the secrets
that Jason's body had given up
during its autopsy.
That Jason didn't die on
July 4th, as we believed,
but over a week later.
♪ Everywhere I look
I catch a glimpse of you
♪ I said it was love
And I did it for love
♪ I did it for you
Subtittle By | SupunWe |