Previously on Riverdale...
Polly's our woman
on the inside.
Blossoms had something
to do with Jason's death.
And I'm gonna prove it.
My dad hired Jughead's dad
to trash the drive-in.
Dad, did you have
anything to do with
Jason Blossom's death?
I'm no killer.
- Do you believe him?
- I do.
Hiram Lodge's
daughter is here.
She said something
about her father being
connected to Jason's murder.
These kids are more
on the ball than the Sheriff.
I'm messed up, Veronica...
Every day I wonder,
what if I had left Riverdale
with my mom?
Hi, honey.
♪ All hail
♪ Our fair Riverdale
♪ My heart rings true ♪
People like
to say that the death
of Jason Blossom
changed everything
at Riverdale High.
But certain things,
certain traditions
never change.
Take Homecoming, for instance.
Though Jason's jersey
had been retired,
the Riverdale Bulldogs
would still be playing
their arch-rivals,
the Baxter High Ravens,
with the River Vixens
cheering them on.
I'm just handing off some of
my decorating duties to Ethel
so I can keep focusing on
the Blue and Gold.
Unacceptable.
You made a commitment,
Ms. Cooper,
you need to honor it.
Especially since
this Homecoming is
also a Reunion Weekend.
As in previous years,
graduates from
days of Riverdale Past
will come to town
to relive their more youthful,
more carefree days.
Or to make up for lost time.
Archie, the reason
why I came...
You came
because of the divorce.
Because I called Dad.
You know, I thought that
Riverdale would be better
for you than Chicago.
- It would be safer...
- It's okay, Mom.
Really, I'm okay.
And I mean,
it hasn't been all bad.
My friends are amazing.
Dad and I are closer than
ever right now. And also...
You've been singing.
Songwriting, yeah.
And singing.
- And your dad tells me
that you're great.
I hope you'll play me
some songs before I go.
Yeah, for sure.
I'm playing at the dance.
So, if you want
to see me play live...
That's incredible, Paul.
You will keep us posted,
won't you?
Okay, thanks... Thank you.
Some good news for a change?
That was your dad's attorney.
Turns out, our statements
did make a difference
and the judge seems
inclined to give
your father a break.
How much of a break?
Time served.
A few more months,
if that.
And then what?
We move back to New York?
Or your father moves here.
What about the crimes
he's committed?
Including, maybe,
Jason Blossom.
Stop it, Veronica.
There is no proof
that your father had
anything to do with that.
He's in jail because of
the Blossoms, Mom,
that gives him a motive.
Okay. Veronica, you need to be
supporting your father,
not demonizing him...
Again, for things that
you have no proof of.
Dad,
have you been body-snatched?
Oh, I feel good, Jug.
Wanna look good, too.
Shave.
Clean the place up a bit.
A little paint...
Oh, I got us some
coffee and donuts.
And I read your, uh...
Your essay?
Manuscript?
- You did?
- Yeah.
- Really?
- I asked you for it, didn't I?
Yeah, I don't know.
I figured you were just
pretending to be interested.
This is excellent.
Me, I can barely
string two sentences together,
but you... You got a gift.
Thank God you're
not wasting it.
Mind if I ask you
a couple questions?
Yeah. Of course.
Why Jason Blossom, huh?
Out of all the things
you could write about,
why pick a dead kid?
I don't know. It was
sort like he picked me.
Tell the story that no one
was gonna tell.
Or even know how to tell.
From the outside, looking in.
Who do you think killed him?
I mean, you and Betty
are in this deep.
You gotta have an opinion.
To me, I don't think
the question is,
"Whodunnit?"
I think the real question is
whether Riverdale
is a place of good
or a place of
darkness and evil.
Or both.
Most things are both.
Can I make one suggestion?
That's what Betty says,
and then it's about
a dozen suggestions.
I think, at a certain point,
you should
move on.
You can't let this be
the only story you're
gonna tell, Jughead.
Hell, it shouldn't even be
the most important one.
Ronnie, wait up.
Hey, I just wanted
to explain why I didn't
call you after the party.
My mom showed up
out of nowhere.
It's fine, you don't
owe me an explanation.
Wait, Veronica,
are we seriously not
gonna talk about what
happened between us?
Archie.
We had a moment.
A beautiful,
but fleeting moment.
- We spent the night.
- We crashed,
in separate beds.
I don't regret anything
we said, Veronica, or did.
Me neither,
but I think you might be
boyfriend-worthy.
I agree. Let's test
that theory at the
Homecoming Dance.
Unfortunately, I don't
have the bandwidth
to explore anything
with anyone right now.
Well, in that case,
what if we just finally get to
sing that duet together?
I kind of told my mom
I was performing.
Look, Archie, I'm sorry,
but for a million reasons,
we're going to have to
pretend our moment
never happened.
I'll see you later.
Oh, finally, close that door.
Ladies, I need you
to look around the room.
Whoever is not in this room
is on the table
as a possible murder suspect.
Including those Pussycats.
Oh, my God, Mom...
Now, let's talk
about your father.
He has an epic grudge
against the Blossoms,
so yes.
It's totally within the
realm of possibility
that he hired someone
from jail to kill Jason.
Maybe Jughead's dad.
You really believe that?
My dad paid Jughead's
dad to trash the drive-in.
- Maybe he paid him to...
- Commit murder.
And, for all we know,
that gay Greaser Serpent
is an accomplice.
And what are you
basing that off of?
That you saw FP
and Joaquin talking?
It didn't look like
they were talking.
It looked like
they were conspiring.
Conspiring about what?
That's what
I need you to find out.
Either through Jughead
or FP directly,
without raising suspicion,
of course.
Which is why I have
prepared a seemingly
innocuous list of questions.
I already asked Jughead,
point-blank,
if he thought his father
had anything to do
with Jason's death,
and he said no.
And I believed him,
and I still believe him.
Betty, you're
too close to this.
I'm not going
to insult Jughead
or betray him
by entertaining this.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have a Homecoming Dance
to plan.
Come on, Vee, let's go.
Mrs. Cooper?
Yes?
I understand why Betty
doesn't want to get
in the middle of this.
But I don't feel the same
loyalty for the Jones
family that she does.
- I'm listening.
- Helping you
find out the truth
about FP will help me find
out the truth about my dad.
And whether or not
he hired FP to kill Jason.
What exactly
are you saying, Veronica?
I'm saying,
if you want to go after
Jughead's dad,
Mrs. Cooper, I'm in.
Sorry to interrupt,
but I have an
announcement to make.
One that tangentially
involves you, Betty.
I'm bringing Polly
to the dance as my date,
and we're campaigning as
co-queens of Homecoming Court.
- Because why?
- Because, Nightmare Smurfette,
by all rights, it should've
been Polly and Jason
on that stage being crowned.
This is the next best thing.
So... Don't forget to vote,
and I'll see
everyone at my coronation!
Betty, about the
Homecoming Dance,
can I play a couple songs?
I kind of told my mom that...
Whoa, you don't want me to?
No, no it's not that, Archie,
it's just, um...
This dance needs to be fun.
And your songs,
as amazing as they are...
They make you wanna
slit your wrists.
- In a good way.
- In an amazing way.
But no need to fret, Betty.
'Cause Archie asked me
to sing with him,
and we're thinking about doing
some upbeat covers.
We are?
Aren't we?
Not that I'm complaining,
Ronnie,
but why the change of heart?
Because I'm hoping
you'll say yes to the
favor I'm about to ask you.
Hey, if it's gonna help you,
then I'm in.
Remember when
you heard Clifford Blossom
say he put my dad in jail?
Well, I think my dad may have
gone after Jason as payback.
He's very eye-for-an-eye,
and I have a strong suspicion
he hired Jughead's dad
to do his dirty work.
Also, FP's done my dad's
bidding before.
He trashed the drive-in.
It's a big leap to go from
vandalism to murder, Ronnie.
I talked it over
with Mrs. Cooper.
- And...
- She's a part of this?
Are you nuts?
She's gonna keep FP busy
while we search his trailer
to find anything
that links FP to Jason.
Or, more importantly,
FP to my dad.
We should
just talk to Jughead.
No, what if he's protecting FP
or tries to warn him?
He's our friend, Ronnie.
My dad is this close
to being released,
and my mom's in denial
and she's ready to welcome
him back with open arms.
Me, I'd like to know
exactly who
we're inviting back
into our lives.
Look, Veronica, I really
wanna help you,
I do, and I definitely don't
want Jughead to get hurt,
but I'm telling you,
FP's cleaned up his act.
I hope you're right
about that, Archie,
because if not,
Jughead could get
dragged into something
very messy and very dangerous.
- Hermione, hi.
- Mary Andrews?
What... What are you
doing in town?
Oh just a
spur-of-the-moment visit.
I was hoping to surprise
Fred with lunch.
Oh, he's off-site.
He's picking up some
supplies from a vendor.
Yeah, he told me that
you were working for him.
With him.
Yeah, he says
he admires your chutzpah.
That's a very
Fred thing to say, huh?
Yeah, but in this case,
I agree.
You know,
I've been following the news.
Yeah.
Karmic payback
for being such a mean girl
in high school, I suppose.
Polly, thank God,
what's going on?
And why are you running
to be Homecoming
co-queen with Cheryl?
To keep her distracted.
Did you find something?
Not yet, but they're
definitely hiding things.
Remember our deal, Polly,
if you don't find anything
by Homecoming, it's over
you're coming home.
I just have to get
into their bedroom.
They protect it obsessively.
Well, you're not putting
yourself in any danger,
are you?
Betty, I gotta go, I'm sorry.
Your daily milkshake.
- You must be famished.
- Mmm-hmm.
What, with all the
exploring you've been doing.
The East Wing,
where Mr. Blossom and I
have our sleeping quarters,
is out of bounds.
Mr. Blossom values
his privacy. You understand.
I'm so sorry.
It won't happen again.
Good.
Thanks.
Hey, you.
- Why didn't you tell me
about the dinner?
- What?
Your mom basically
tackled me in the hall
to invite my dad and I
over before the dance.
- Did you not know?
- No, no, of course, I've just,
you know, got so many...
Plates are spinning...
I'm a little terrified
about the social
experiment of it all,
but I think it's good
for our families to
get to know each other.
I think it's important
for us. You know?
Yeah.
I know what you're doing, Mom.
Whatever do you mean?
I'm making peach pie
for our guests.
No, you're laying out
some kind of trap
for Jughead's dad.
On the contrary, Betty,
I took what you said
earlier to heart.
So you're not going to
question Jughead or his dad
about the murder then?
I mean, only if it happens
to come up as casual
dinner conversation.
I'm not playing this game
with you, Mom.
And neither is Jughead,
not after I tell him
what you're planning here.
Are you sure
that's a good idea, Betty?
When I invited Jughead,
he seemed so excited.
Like it really
meant a lot to him
that our families are gonna
get to know each other.
That's all I'm after, honey.
FP is innocent, Mom.
Jughead said so,
and I trust him.
I'm sure the question of FP's
guilt or innocence
won't even come up at dinner.
Now, this is
pretty good.
Oh, there he is.
Son, your mom and I
are trying to decide between
pizza and Chinese food.
- What do you think?
- Uh... We always do pizza.
Let me guess.
Pepperoni and red pepper?
All right, so, Moon Palace,
they still deliver.
- We can get, um...
- General Tso's chicken,
scallion pancakes,
vegetable dumplings,
family-style.
What's wrong, son?
Huh? Nothing.
I'm just... I'm not used
to coming home and
seeing you guys together.
It's nice, but...
- Hello?
- Jughead, hey.
Am I interrupting
a family meeting?
'Cause I can come back.
Absolutely not.
So, who's going to the dance?
Besides your dad and me...
Oh, and Hermione,
whom I invited.
- You did?
- We'll talk about it.
Wait, you guys are going
to the dance? Together?
We were talking about it.
We both want to hear you play,
if that's still happening.
If you're good with it.
Yeah, totally.
I'm great with it.
- Good.
- So the worm turns.
Mary and Fred.
A possible rekindling?
That would've been
a Li'l Archie's pipe dream.
Stranger things have
happened, man.
Like for instance,
my dad shaved.
Which is the equivalent
of tectonic plates shifting.
I was thinking,
maybe it's time I go back
and live with him again.
Based on the fact
that he shaved?
Well, he also hasn't missed
a day of work,
and he quit drinking.
That's...
That's great, Jughead.
But maybe you should wait
a little bit longer just to
make sure it sticks.
No, dude, I'm telling you,
something has shifted.
I mean, he even asked
to read my work.
The essays, the articles
I wrote about Jason.
- Your dad did?
- Yeah.
And he read them.
Even more surprisingly,
he engaged with them.
He asked me
questions about them.
- What kind of questions?
- Like who I thought did it.
Your dad asked you
who you thought
killed Jason Blossom?
You repeating everything
I'm saying is getting
really annoying.
Crap, I forgot. My mom likes
almond milk in her coffee,
and we don't have any, so...
I'm gonna go get some.
Well, you are
a terrible liar, Archie.
Off to a late-night
rendezvous with a certain
raven-haired princess?
Relax, man, I'm just giving
you a hard time.
Archie.
If this is a booty call...
Look, I've been thinking about
what you asked me.
I wanna help you.
What prompted
this return to sanity?
Jughead.
He's been hurt and
let down by his dad
so many times.
And what if FP
did help your dad?
That's what I'm saying,
what if?
But, Veronica...
Jughead can never find out.
And neither can Betty.
Oh, Pollikins,
it's much more fun
being friends
than mortal enemies.
And I'm glad we're honoring
Jay-Jay's legacy together.
This color
totally pops on you.
Okay, so I was thinking.
The theme for the dance is
"Blast from the Past," right?
So, I say, we go
retro and borrow
some of your mom's
vintage bling for the night.
Ooh, you're naughty, Polly.
My mom and dad
would fah-reak if
they knew we were in here.
So let's take our sweet time.
How many wigs
does your father have?
One for every mood.
Legend has it
that Clifford's hair
turned white overnight.
Supposedly, he saw the
ghost of Grandpappy Blossom
with his throat slit.
Now, me, I love a silver fox,
but we Blossoms live
and die by our red curls.
My father tried
dying it once, but...
But what?
What is that?
What did you find?
My nana's ring...
Which she gave to Jason.
He... He proposed to me
with that ring.
So how does
your mother have it?
I...
Hands off, Gollum.
The only way your mom
could have that ring
is if she or your dad
got it from Jason,
and he wouldn't
have given it up.
Not over his dead body.
Polly...
You are carrying
precious cargo,
but if you think
for one second
that those babies guarantee
your safety,
you're in for a
rude awakening.
Super-delicious, Mrs. C.
Sure is, Alice.
Been a long time
since I ate something
that didn't come in a
combo meal or a snack pack.
- So, FP...
- Mmm.
Betty tells me that you're
working for Fred Andrews now.
How do you balance
that with all of your
other responsibilities?
You mean like
being a father?
- And being a part of the
Southside community.
- Mom.
You can say
"Southside Serpent," Alice.
I'm not ashamed.
And it's not just me,
there's a bunch of us
working on Fred's site.
So, if you don't mind
me asking, I mean,
I'm just curious,
how did you make
your living before that?
I scraped by. Odd jobs.
I know that you
worked for the drive-in,
Jughead, before it was closed.
Did you find
work there, too, FP?
- Dad.
- Well, hung out a bit.
What can I say?
I'm a movie buff.
So, tell me,
were you upset
when Hiram Lodge
bought the drive-in land?
Stuff happens.
Let me rephrase that question.
Were you surprised?
I'll get it.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Right this way.
I thought you said she
wanted me to be here.
She does.
I mean, it is Homecoming
after all.
And our families should be
coming together.
Right, Mom?
It's the same as when
we were kids.
You start in the bedroom,
I'll start in here.
You wanted an explanation.
The last time
Clifford saw Jason
was the day my son washed
his hands of our family.
Jason wanted nothing more to
do with the Blossom name,
nor our lineage.
Including the ring,
which he threw in Clifford's
face as his final rebuke.
Clifford then gave the ring
to me for safekeeping.
I...
I thought the ring
had been lost...
Nothing's lost forever.
Everything comes back.
Now. Unless you have
any more questions,
I'll leave you to finish
getting ready for the dance.
And drink up, dear.
Before it melts.
I'm hoping maybe you have some
vacancies down at Sunnyside.
You see, I've been
sleeping in my office
down at the paper,
and it's just getting a little
chilly at night.
I bet your office
beats the trailer park.
I wouldn't be so sure.
You see, Alice here,
she's been redecorating
the Register.
The other day, she threw
a brick through the window.
- Is that so?
- Keep talking, Hal,
and the next brick I throw
may not be at a window.
You remember
our Homecoming, Alice?
Hal? Back in the day?
Castles in the Clouds?
Your mom ever tell you
about that night?
Just that she and my dad
were king and queen.
Yeah, they were. Of hell.
- Dad, please.
- No, this is a fun story,
I promise.
Fred and me,
we were all set
to play at the dance.
I was backstage,
dropping off our gear
when I heard
these voices yelling.
It was your mom and dad.
They were fighting about...
About I don't know what.
But it sounded like
life or death.
Shut up, FP.
Happy to oblige if you are.
I don't care what you
think of me, Alice,
but don't jerk me around.
Not in front of my son.
This was such
a nice idea, Mom,
but I think it's time that
we get to the dance.
So, is it okay if we
skip the peach pie?
What did you give her?
Polly was so agitated,
I gave her an
all-natural relaxer.
Nothing to hurt the babies,
but she will sleep
like a lamb till morning.
Was that story true?
About how you
got the ring back?
Every word of it.
You know,
your brother rejected us,
our way of life,
our business, everything.
And after I had groomed him
to take over the empire.
When really, I should have
been nurturing you.
Jason never had
the stomach for any of it.
But you...
You're a Blossom,
through and through.
Okay.
One more thing
before you go to the dance.
Nana Blossom's ring...
It's not in my jewelry box,
it's not with Polly.
Where is it?
It wasn't my fault,
it was Polly's.
She lunged at me,
trying to get it,
I didn't know what to do.
I panicked.
I thought it would be
better for everyone
if the ring were just gone.
Down the drain.
That way, if Polly ever
said anything to anyone,
there'd be no proof.
Just her word
against ours.
Did I do something wrong?
No...
It's quite right what you did.
Look, I checked everywhere.
Twice.
But there's nothing weird
or dangerous-looking.
Same out here,
just tumbleweeds
and dust bunnies, that's it.
- We need to keep looking.
- Veronica.
- Somewhere, there's
something that proves it.
- What?
What are we even
looking for, Ronnie?
A signed contract between
Jughead's dad and yours?
I doubt they're that stupid...
We'll switch... I'll take
the bedroom this time.
You wanted to see if we would
find anything incriminating,
and we didn't.
Then we'll look
somewhere else.
Outside or under the trailer.
Veronica,
what do you want?
Do you want your dad
to be guilty?
I want to know, Archie.
One way or the other,
I need to be sure.
We can keep looking
forever, Ronnie,
and never find anything.
Then what about
when he comes home?
I'm not sure.
But I'll be right
there, next to you,
doing what I can
to help. If you'll let me.
And maybe I'm wrong,
but not finding anything
tonight feels like a win.
A major win for the home team.
What?
Just...
"Yea, though I walk through
the Valley of Darkness,
"and Archie Andrews
is there with a smile
and a sports metaphor."
It's Mrs. Cooper.
We need to go, right now.
FP could be on his way home,
let's go.
You be a gentleman
tonight, okay?
He always is, Mr. Jones.
Betty, would you mind
giving us just a minute?
No, of course. Take your time.
Thank you.
What's up?
Look, I've been thinking.
I mean, if it's
all right with you...
I could come back.
And I could... I could
come back home.
I'll do you one better.
It's time the whole family
gets back together.
Us, your mom, Jellybean.
They've got a
sweet set-up in Toledo,
- there's decent work there...
- In Toledo?
Well, why not Riverdale?
'Cause of dinners
like we just had.
And what you're writing
about in your book.
And hell, you know
what happens to people
like us in Riverdale, Jug.
We get chewed up.
Well, it's not
the Met Ball, but...
Thanks for letting me
tag along, Fred.
It was Mary's idea.
Always like to have a
beautiful woman on my arm.
Tonight, I have two.
Meanwhile, I'm having
major deja vu.
Remember when
this was our lives?
The best of times...
Betty, tonight after
the dance, I'd like to talk
to you about something.
It has to do with my dad.
Is everything okay?
Yeah...
Actually, things are great.
Better than they've been
in a while.
I just kind of wanna figure
something out together.
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, God...
Will you be okay alone
here for a second?
I think I should be fine.
I'll be right back.
Cheryl? Hey. Where's Polly?
She's fine.
She sugar-crashed and
canceled at the last minute,
leaving me high and dry,
which is why I'm never
doing anything nice
for anyone ever again.
Excuse me.
Well, well, well...
Mary Andrews.
Alice Cooper.
Saw you swanning in earlier
with Fred and Hermione.
I didn't realize that you were
a polyamorist.
I don't think that's
an actual word.
- It's a compliment, Mary.
- Huh.
I couldn't be seen in the
same room with those two.
Not after all their
monkey business.
Oh...
Oh... Did you not know?
You have been playing
the same game
since junior high
and it was tired
even back then.
Fred is a big boy,
he can do as he pleases.
I came here tonight
to have fun
with both of my dates.
So, if you have
a problem with that...
I have to take this.
Hey, Kev...
Have you seen Archie
and Veronica?
Oh, never mind, I see them.
What the hell?
There you are, Ms. Cooper.
Mayor McCoy would like
to review the evening's
itinerary with you.
What can I do for you,
Mayor McCoy?
Well, firstly,
I was wondering...
- Would you walk me up?
- I'm sorry. What?
To the stage?
Oh...
Actually,
Principal Weatherbee,
will you do the honors?
I have to... Go.
Excuse me.
Where were you guys?
We stopped...
We stopped at Pop's.
And what were you
just talking to my mom about?
- Betty...
- Guys, can we table this?
We gotta get ready.
Come on.
Friends, students and alumni.
I hope you brought
your dancing shoes.
Please join me in
welcoming to the stage
Riverdale High's very own
Archie Andrews and
Veronica Lodge!
♪ Looking out a
dirty old window
♪ Down below the cars
in the city go rushing by
♪ I sit here alone
and I wonder why
♪ Friday night and
everyone's moving
♪ I can feel the heat,
but it's soothing
♪ Heading down
♪ I search for the beat
in this dirty town
♪ Downtown the young ones
are going
are...
I got a warrant to
search the premises.
Be my guest.
I got nothing to hide.
♪ We're the kids in America
Whoa-oh
♪ Everybody live
for the music-go-round
♪ Bright lights
The music gets faster
♪ Look boy, don't check
on your watch
♪ Not another glance
♪ I'm not leaving now,
honey, not a chance
♪ Hotshot,
give me no problems
♪ Much later, baby,
you'll be saying never mind
♪ You know life is cruel
Life is never kind
♪ Kind hearts don't make
a new story
♪ Kind hearts
don't grab any glory
♪ We're the kids in America
Whoa-oh
♪ Everybody live
for the music-go-round
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la, la
♪ La, la, la, la, la
♪ Come closer,
honey, that's better
♪ Got to get a
brand-new experience
♪ Feeling right
♪ Oh, don't try to stop, baby
♪ Hold me tight
♪ Outside a new day is dawning
♪ Outside suburbia's
sprawling everywhere
♪ I don't want to go, baby
♪ New York to East California
♪ There's a new wave
coming, I warn you
♪ We're the kids in America
Whoa-oh
♪ Everybody live
for the music-go-round
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la, la
♪ La, la, la, la, la
You want to explain this?
♪ La, la, la, la, la ♪
So, Archie and Veronica are...
We haven't exactly had
the conversation,
but the Magic 8-Ball says,
"Yes."
You Andrews men
are such players.
This is the first time
I've brought a boyfriend
to one of these things.
This is the first time
I've really had a boyfriend.
Mostly it's been hook-ups
with closeted guys.
Hey, guys, sorry to interrupt.
Have you seen Betty anywhere?
You all need tracking devices.
I think she was headed out
to the hall with Veronica
and maybe Archie.
Thanks.
Before you get mad,
let me explain.
Explain what?
That you're working with
my mom behind my back?
I'm sorry, Bee, but you know
FP had some kind of
arrangement with my dad.
I had to make sure it wasn't
about Jason Blossom.
And what's your excuse?
I was looking out for
Jughead in case FP
was doing shady stuff.
- To protect him.
- Blame me, Betty.
I asked Archie to help me.
Help you do what?
What did you two do?
Guys... Betty...
What's going on?
Why do I feel like I'm
suddenly left out?
Do you want to tell him
or should I?
Tell me what?
We went to your
dad's trailer to...
To search it, Jughead.
- Why would you guys do that?
- My mom put them up to it.
She was
convinced he was hiding
something about Jason.
We were wrong. All of us.
We didn't find anything.
And Jug, we were only
doing it to prove that...
That my dad wasn't a murderer?
- You went behind
my back, Archie?
- Jug...
How did you...
When did you guys know
to go to my dad's trailer?
We knew he'd be
at dinner with...
No...
That's why your mom invited
my dad and I to dinner?
So these two could
break into his trailer
while she interrogated him?
No, I didn't know
what they were doing.
But yes, that is why
she invited you guys.
To think I was gonna pass
on moving to Toledo
with my family for you.
What?
When we went to my
dad's trailer, you asked
me if I believed him.
I said I did.
- Wasn't that
good enough for you?
- It was. It was good enough.
I didn't...
I tried to stop her.
You could've told me,
you could've warned
me about this.
You were so excited, Jug,
I didn't want to
disappoint you.
So instead you lied?
- You all lied to me?
- There they are.
- Betty. Thank God...
- Mom, don't...
No, you have to listen.
All of you.
My dad just told Mayor McCoy
about your dad, Jughead.
What about my dad?
He was just arrested.
For the murder of
Jason Blossom.
I'm not a perfect father,
Jughead, no getting
around that, but...
I'm no killer.
Kevin said someone tipped off
his dad, was it you?
- I was at the dance, Betty...
- Answer the damn
question, Mom.
And don't lie.
Was it you?
It was not.
But I'm glad that you're safe.
And as much as I like Jughead,
- I am so glad that you are
done with that family.
- "Done"?
I love Jughead.
He's as much my
family as you are,
more so right now.
You are not going anywhere,
young lady.
I am going to look
for Jughead.
Do not push me tonight, Mom,
because I will push back.
If FP confesses, he might
drag us into this.
Talk about our dealings
with the Serpents.
But at least we'll know
if Dad hired him to...
And if he did?
And you can't
pretend otherwise?
We'll cut all ties with him.
He'll be dead to us.
We may not be able
to walk away so easily.
FP has always
had his demons.
I really thought he'd
changed, Mom, I...
It's very hard for people
to change, Archie.
You know, after
I heard you play
and before everything
happened,
I was going to ask you
to come to Chicago with me.
To stay.
You could study music.
I'm not even thinking
about that right now, Mom.
No, I know, I know.
It's just,
I want you with me.
I don't think that this town
is safe anymore.
I feel like Riverdale is
getting ready to
slide off of a mountainside,
and I don't want you anywhere
around when that happens.
Just promise me you'll
at least think about it.
Yeah, I will.
That bastard
killed my baby.
He killed my Jason.
I want him dead
for what he did.
You have my word, darling.
You have my word.
Pop... Jughead hasn't
been by, has he?
Nope. You're not the
only one who's come
looking for him.
Betty...
- Thank goodness.
- We were gonna call you.
I'm not talking to you,
either of you, ever again.
It's about Jughead.
Kevin called me. And he said
his dad found a gun,
the gun that killed Jason,
in a lockbox in FP's closet.
But Betty, we searched
FP's trailer.
We looked through that closet.
And there was no lockbox.
Someone put it there
after we left.
He's being framed.