Previously on Riverdale...
The story is about a town,
once wholesome and innocent,
now forever changed
by the mysterious death
of Jason Blossom
on the 4th of July.
- Can we talk, Ms. Grundy?
- About what?
You're the music teacher.
Can we talk about music?
We heard what we heard,
and afterwards
we didn't do anything!
How would we explain why
we were together at 6:00 a.m.
on the 4th of July?
- Hello, Fred.
- Can I get you anything?
- A job.
- I can't very well have
the wife of Hiram Lodge,
on trial for fraud
and embezzlement,
balancing my books.
Oh, Hiram...
Oh, my God, it's Jason.
He was shot.
What were you doing
down at the river so early
on July 4th?
- Working on some songs.
- Were you alone?
I saw something
at Sweetwater River.
Ms. Grundy's car.
By the river's edge.
It's been
a week since the discovery
of Jason Blossom's body.
But his death
is not the first,
nor would it be
the last casualty
that the town of
Riverdale would suffer.
The Twilight Drive-In
where I work,
my home away from home,
a piece of town history,
is closing for good,
just when we needed
a place to escape to the most.
With Sheriff Keller
knocking on every door
and neighbor
suspecting neighbor,
Riverdale, every day
that passes, is becoming
more like Salem
during the witch trials.
And meanwhile,
the girl next door,
our friendly neighborhood
Hitchcock blonde,
Betty Cooper,
was wrestling
with the knowledge
that her best friend,
Archie Andrews,
was caught up in
a forbidden romance.
"Dear Diary,
"Sheriff Keller doesn't
know what I know,
"that Riverdale High's
music teacher,
Geraldine Grundy,
"was at Sweetwater River
the morning
Jason Blossom went missing,
"and that since Archie
was also there,
"they could have
been there together."
She is incredible.
She's the best.
I'm usually more
of a classic rock kind of guy,
but that was beautiful.
Truly.
Congratulations, Ms. Grundy.
Thank you,
both of you for coming.
No, you kidding?
Archie, he wouldn't miss it.
I had to beg him
to let me come.
Great. I'll see you
at school, Ms. Grundy.
Let's go, Dad.
Well, I was thinkin' that,
you know,
if you're gonna
be alone tonight,
that we could take you
out to dinner.
Oh. No, I...
No, I couldn't impose.
After everything
you've done for my son, I...
You know, with his music,
it's the least
I can do. I insist.
The Drive-In closing
is just one more
nail in the coffin
that is Riverdale...
No, forget Riverdale,
in the coffin of
the American dream.
As the godfather of
indie cinema,
Quentin Tarantino,
likes to say...
Please, God,
no more
Quentin Tarantino references.
What? I'm pissed.
And not just
about losing my job.
The Twilight Drive-In
should mean
something to us.
People should be
trying to save it.
In this age of Netflix
and VOD,
do people
really want to watch
a movie in a car?
I mean, who even goes there?
People who
want to buy crack.
And cinephiles,
and car enthusiasts.
Right, Bets?
Totally.
Anyway, it's closing
because the town owns it,
but didn't invest in it.
So when an anonymous buyer
made Mayor McCoy an offer,
she couldn't refuse...
Anonymous buyer?
What do they
have to hide?
No one cares.
I do!
Also, you guys should
all come to closing night.
I'm thinking
American Graffiti...
Or is that
too obvious?
I vote for anything
starring Audrey Hepburn.
Or Cate Blanchett.
Or The Talented Mr. Ripley.
Betty, your choices?
Everything okay, B?
Yeah, I'm just thinking. Um...
Maybe
Rebel Without a Cause?
Here you go, kids.
Thanks, Mom.
If I would have known
Mama Lodge was working
as a waitress at Pop's,
I never would have
given Veronica
a spot on the Vixens.
It's off-brand,
and sends a false message
about acceptance.
After her TMZ-style
take-down of Chuck,
all the Vixens kind of
like Veronica now.
Do they?
Be sure to put
all that cash
in the register.
You are a Lodge, after all,
and Lodges are known
to have sticky fingers.
- Cheryl...
- Honey, I got this.
Cheryl, I went to school
with your mother.
She didn't know the difference
between having money
and having class, either.
Now, that's an odd
combo of people.
- I'll be right back.
- No, Betty.
No. Don't...
Wait, what's happening?
Hey, Betty.
Hi, Mr. Andrews,
Ms. Grundy.
Archie, can I talk to you?
Sure. I'll call you later?
No. Actually, now.
Just school stuff. Outside?
Archie, as your best friend,
is there anything
you want to tell me?
I don't think so.
Ms. Grundy was at
Sweetwater River on July 4th.
Were you with her?
Did Jughead tell you?
Jughead knows about this?
What's happening out there?
Do we know? Is it about me?
I have a strong inkling,
and no.
Also, I'd let it go.
Yes, but you're you,
and I'm me.
You do you, girl,
I'll be back.
What was it like
before she got here?
I honestly cannot remember.
It's not what you're thinking.
So, it's platonic?
Okay, well, maybe
it's a little like
- what you're thinking...
- Archie.
Are you and Ms. Grundy,
like, together,
like, romantically?
Oh, my God.
You and your music teacher
are having an affair?
We are...
...together. Look,
I know that sounds bad, but...
Bad?
It sounds scandalous.
It sounds like
jail time to me. Illegal!
- Betty, don't go there.
- Oh, I'm already there.
Ronnie, a little help here?
I mean,
technically, Betty's right.
And ethically...
Well, what is Grundy
to you, anyway,
your girlfriend?
Your booty tutor?
I don't know,
I don't know
what to call her.
You said you were
at the river alone.
You lied to Sheriff Keller,
to all of us.
Why? To protect her?
She believed in me
when no one else did.
Okay, we get it.
Betty, say something, please.
Get in the car, Betty. Now.
- What have I told you
about those two?
- Can we just go?
Oh, Archiekins...
You're in it deep this time.
Turn down the music.
I spy with my little eye
Hermione Lodge,
full of secrets.
Riddle me this,
hair models
of the damned,
why is Veronica's mother
having a clandestine
tete-a-tete
with a Southside Serpent
behind a dumpster at Pop's?
Yeah, so we agree.
How hard would it
have been to give me
a little heads-up?
Look, I am, by nature,
a conscientious objector.
Not saying anything
to either you or Betty,
was the most moral, apathetic
choice I could make.
But, Jug.
She's not going to write
about me and Grundy
in the paper, is she?
Like she did with Chuck?
Dude, seriously?
Okay. Come on.
Think about
what you're asking.
If there was even
an iota of a chance
that something could
hurt you in any way,
Betty wouldn't do it.
- Probably.
- Oh, my God.
I'm kidding.
But maybe she has a point.
What do you see happening
with Grundy, long-term?
What do you want?
I want
to be with her.
I don't know how,
but I wanna hang on to
what we have for
as long as possible.
Yup. I feel that.
Trying to hold on
to something a lot
older than me, too.
Just... If Betty's gonna
do anything crazy,
can you please
let me know so I can
do something to stop it?
Thank you for taking
the time, Ms. Grundy.
Like I said,
the Blue and Gold
is doing
a series of articles
spotlighting teachers,
and you're our first.
Let's begin.
Uh, you joined
the faculty last year.
Where did you move
to Riverdale from?
Um, here and there. I was
just mostly on the road.
- But you've taught at other
schools, I'm assuming?
- Oh, yeah. Of course.
- Yeah.
- Right.
Um...
Can I get their names?
Seaside High,
Centreville High.
What made you leave?
They were temporary
placements.
Just filling in for
maternity, sabbatical,
things like that.
This is my first
permanent position.
Getting back to music,
you're working
with Archie Andrews
on an independent study.
Have you ever done
this sort of thing before?
- Yes. Last year.
- Oh.
With Tomoko Yoshido
and Jason Blossom.
Jason?
- Before...
- Such a tragedy.
He was an inspiration.
And pretty cute, right?
I don't think of
my students that way.
- No, no, no, no...
- And I'm sorry,
I really should
prepare for
my next class.
It's this quintessential
rite of passage,
making out with your boy
or girlfriend at the movies.
Why don't we go together?
I can't promise you
any action,
but maybe I'll bring you
good luck.
Great. Another night,
another hag.
Speaking of hags...
Veronica,
it's so devastating to me
that your mother
has to sink to such
unspeakable lows
just to keep those knockoff
Hermes bags on your arm.
What's next, selling
her hair extensions?
My mom's a waitress,
Cheryl, not Fantine.
And your faux concern
reeks of ulterior motive.
What is it?
Only to remind you
of your place in this school,
nay, the town's
social hierarchy.
Threatened much?
Don't worry.
You may be a stock character
from a '90s teen movie,
but I'm not.
And what does
any of this have to do
with my mom
being a waitress?
It's just that
I saw her talking to
a Southside Serpent
last night,
in the alley behind Pop's.
They were having an extremely
heated, intimate discussion.
See for yourself.
Who or what is
a Southside Serpent?
They're this
gang of bikers
who pretty much stays
on the south side of town.
And thank God, 'cause
they're sort of dangerous.
Drug dealers
and petty thieves.
Then what was my mom
doing with one of them?
Ugh.
Who knew
working would be so...
Tiring.
- Mom.
- Hmm?
Cheryl showed me a picture.
You were standing
behind Pop's
with a Southside Serpent.
Those guys are thugs.
What were you doing?
First off, you have
nothing to worry about.
Come here, sit.
Now, remember Veronica,
I grew up here.
The Southside Serpents may be
from the wrong
side of the tracks,
but I went to high school
with some of them.
I was just being polite.
Cheryl said it looked
like you were arguing.
Arguing?
Hardly.
He made a lewd comment,
and I put him in his place.
- Mom, if you're in some
kind of trouble...
- I'm not.
Mija.
And when have
I ever lied to you?
I'm sorry,
but the Twilight Drive-In?
It's a blight
that's become a cesspool,
and a hangout
for criminals...
...and transients,
and the deal's done.
Andrews Construction
is scheduled
to demolish
the lot on Monday.
Mayor McCoy,
when I was a kid,
my family and I would go
to the drive-in all the time.
We couldn't afford
tickets for everyone,
so my sister
Jellybean and I would
hide in the trunk
until we parked.
We'd sneak out.
It's like my home.
That's a very sweet
sentiment, Mr. Jones.
But the future of
Riverdale is at stake.
Ms. Grundy showed up
in Riverdale a year ago,
out of thin air.
There's no record
of her before that.
Her Facebook,
her Linkedln account,
they were all created
one year ago.
Before that, she's a ghost.
She doesn't exist.
The only Geraldine Grundy
I could find was
a woman who died
seven years ago.
How... Where did you
find all this?
The deep web.
The dark internet.
Check it, it's all online.
Simple googling.
And did you cyber-stalk
Ms. Grundy before
or after you interviewed her
for a fake article?
Why are you doing this, Betty?
- I'm not in any danger.
- You don't know that.
Yeah, I do,
I'm with her.
I know
what we have,
and you don't.
She taught Jason Blossom.
- Did you know that?
- She's taught a lot of people,
Betty. What's your point?
My point is,
you don't know anything
about her, Archie.
- Doesn't that worry you?
- Betty, let this go.
- Archie, please...
- If you're really my friend,
you'll let this go.
Okay.
I'm sorry. I'm done.
I'll stop digging.
I know
it's not the drive-in,
but given our circumstances...
It's perfect.
Is everything okay?
We've always been
so focused on me,
my music, we never
get to talk about
you and your life.
- What do you wanna know?
- I dunno.
Stuff.
Anything. Have you always
wanted to be a teacher?
No.
No, I, um...
I graduated Juilliard,
and I auditioned
at Carnegie Hall,
Lincoln Center,
all the big symphonies,
but I didn't
make the cut.
Not even close.
I had a dream.
Sometimes that's all they are.
Just dreams.
And what about us?
Is this a dream?
Would that be so bad?
If it is...
It's a nice dream.
Where does
this end, Geraldine?
I have no idea.
But we're here.
And for me...
That's enough.
So much for
letting this go.
Are we really breaking
into Grundy's car right now?
How do you even know
how to do that?
My dad and I
fix cars together.
Thank God,
she drives an old...
Okay, before
going any further,
if I'm committing a felony,
I need to at least
ask the question.
Are you doing this
because you still have
feelings for Archie, or...
No, Veronica.
We're doing this because
Grundy has Archie
under some kind of
sexual spell,
and he won't listen to reason.
We're looking for anything
that proves Grundy isn't
as clean as she says she is.
Bobby pin.
Okay, Ms. Gyver.
I learned that
from the Nancy Drew
- detective handbook.
- Okay, go.
Oh, my God.
"Jennifer Gibson"?
Who the hell is
Jennifer Gibson?
That's not the only thing.
Oh, God.
Please don't tell me
you're still on
this crazy witch hunt.
It's not a witch hunt,
and it's not crazy.
- We were just in
Grundy's car...
- What?
- You were in her car?
- Yeah,
and thank God we were.
- We found a gun.
- What?
And an ID with
the name Jennifer Gibson.
This is proof
Ms. Grundy is not
who she says she is.
- Then who is she?
- Obviously some sketch-queen
named Jennifer Gibson.
Archie, what if
she had something to do
with Jason's murder?
She taught him,
she made you lie about him,
we know she was
at the river, she has a gun.
So does Dilton Doiley,
but you never thought
he killed Jason.
Open your eyes, Archie.
Jason was her
student last year.
Everything about her
is a huge, boldfaced
question mark.
Okay, whatever her name is,
she's not a killer.
You didn't ask her, did you?
About her name?
And why there's no record
of her before last year?
Why not?
Mayor McCoy says
you won the contract
to tear down the drive-in.
I did.
Look, I'm sorry, Jughead.
I know how much
you love the Twilight,
and so do I...
Mr. Andrews,
just give me one week
to track down
the person who bought
the land, and convince them
not to demolish
a holy house of cinema.
It's a big contract
for me, Jug,
and for my guys.
Whatever they build
in the place of the drive-in
- could mean more jobs...
- Yeah, in what?
Some hypothetical future?
You put one Jones out of work,
why don't you put out
another, huh?
Jug, your dad was
taking materials
from one of our job sites.
I had to let him go.
Right.
You did what you had to do,
like you're doing here now.
Later.
Jug.
You're late, Hermione.
I had to make a pit stop.
And as we discussed,
Madam Mayor...
A donation to your
re-election campaign.
And Lodge Industries
gets the Twilight Drive-In.
It's one of the most
prime pieces
of real estate in Riverdale.
No one can know
that I helped
goose this deal along.
Especially not the Blossoms.
Your secret will be
safe with me,
so long as you hold up
your end of the bargain.
Are you just
gonna stand there?
Archie...
Talk to me.
What is it?
Is your real name
Jennifer Gibson?
Who are you?
And what are you
really doing here?
- Archie...
- Why the new identity,
the moving place-to-place?
Tell me the truth, please.
I
was in a bad relationship.
A relationship...
I was married
to a man who would come home
from work every night, late,
and drunk, and with a temper.
One night, I ended up
in the emergency room
with broken ribs and
a shattered collarbone.
The next morning, he barely
even remembered the fight,
and he promised
that it wouldn't
happen again.
But...
It did,
again.
So...
I left.
And I
got a divorce,
changed my name...
Then I came here.
And I...
Well...
I met you.
Nice murder wall,
True Detective.
- Here's your High Point, Dad.
- Thanks, bud.
You need somethin'?
Can I borrow the truck
for the drive-in?
- You got a date?
- No, I'm going with Veronica.
Oh, okay.
I mean, is there not a
nice gay kid at your school?
Yeah. There is.
Me.
All right.
No cruising guys tonight.
Okay? We both know
what goes on
in those woods.
- Oh, my God, Dad...
- No, I'm dead serious.
All right, we've got
a murderer on the loose
and a lot of unsavory
characters in that
part of town.
So, if you go,
you stay in the truck.
- All right.
- Okay?
Together.
We're sorry to come
unannounced, Fred.
It's been a rough
couple of months for us,
- but Alice and I...
- We think that
Archie and Betty
should stop
spending time together.
Their relationship isn't good,
for either of them,
and their respective
behavior reflects that.
All right. So, if there
was anything that
you could do on your end...
My son's a good kid.
I live next door, Fred.
I see him
sneaking out at night,
slinking off into
the darkness at all hours.
Alice...
Are you spying on us?
Come on, Hal.
We said what
we came to say,
it's on him
if he ignores us.
Oh, my God.
Intense, right?
That's why she has
a fake identity
and keeps a gun.
It still doesn't make
what she did to you okay.
She didn't do anything.
Betty, you have to
accept that.
And I'm all
she has, right now.
You're in
over your head, Arch.
You're in this relationship
with this person
who is cutting you off
from everyone else
in your life.
Just think about
what you're doing, Archie.
Not only for your sake,
but Ms. Grundy's.
Is this really
what's best for her?
I am gonna
deal with this,
but on my terms,
not yours.
Good day, Ms. Hermione.
From the dry cleaners.
Ah, thank you, Smithers.
And Fred Andrews
is escorting me
to the drive-in, so
all the pieces are in place.
- The drive-in with
Fred Andrews?
- Yes.
An attractive woman going with
an old friend is
less conspicuous
than an old crone going alone.
You're not
an old crone,
Ms. Hermione.
Of course not.
That was a joke.
- Finally.
- What's wrong?
What's wrong is my daughter
is hiding a gun
in her bedroom,
and that's just for starters.
- I can explain...
- Oh, you will.
Now, get in the car.
Make some room, outcasts.
I'm having deja vu.
Yeah, senior year,
we're here, watching Candyman.
God, I hated that movie.
- You picked it.
- Mmm.
Did you think
I'd get scared,
and jump into your arms
like a damsel
in distress?
You did kiss me that night.
The briefest of flings.
You kissed me.
Is everything all right?
Yes.
I'm still hungry.
I'm gonna get
some popcorn.
- Oh, I'll come.
- No.
It's fine. I'm gonna
powder my nose.
Excuse me.
- Alice!
- I'm sorry to interrupt
your adultery, Fred,
but you need to
come with me.
Alice, what...
It's about the kids.
That hair.
That jacket.
Jason always
adored the drive-in.
Southside trash.
They've been doing that
since the opening credits.
Shh!
- Screw off!
- Nice haircut, you dweeb.
Hey! You know
what happens to a snake
when a Louis Vuitton
heel steps on it?
Shut the hell up,
or you'll find out!
Thank you.
I cannot believe you just
threatened a gang-banger.
I've dealt with worse
in the East Village.
I just hate when
people disrespect
my cinematic experience.
How about a refill?
Yeah, Kev,
how about a refill?
Cherry cola, as always.
Can I get a refill?
And some
gummy worms
and a cola.
And a hot dog?
Who am I trying to impress?
We're out of dogs.
Figures.
Not so tough without
your beard, huh?
Where's the rest of it?
The rest of it?
It was my understanding that
that was the agreed-upon
amount.
In that case,
maybe we need to have
a word with your husband.
Good luck with that.
As long as Hiram's in jail,
you'll be dealing with me.
Mmm-hmm.
- Is that a problem?
- Mmm.
Enjoy the movie, Hermione.
We'll be in touch.
No drive-in for you tonight?
I got you something.
Is this to make me feel better
about my tragic past?
No.
It's a...
It's a thank-you gift
for everything
you've done for me.
Archie...
This...
You cannot afford this.
I pawned one of my guitars.
Why?
You don't need to thank me.
You shouldn't...
...thank me.
Ms. Grundy,
I don't, I don't want to end
our lessons, but...
But that's what
you think we should do?
Don't you?
So, that bow
is a goodbye gift?
It's a
see-you-around-the-halls
gift.
A don't-forget-me gift.
That is hardly likely.
Well, well, well.
There they are.
What did I tell you?
Can someone tell me
what's going on here?
Of course. Archie,
would you like to
share with us
what you and Mrs. Robinson
have been doing
during your "music lesson"?
And please don't leave out
any of the lurid details,
because Betty here
keeps a very meticulous diary,
and I'm more than happy
to fill in the details.
Okay, okay.
This time I really need to go.
I'm Joaquin, by the way.
Give me your phone.
This is my number.
Use it.
Kevin Keller...
As in Sheriff Keller?
Is that a problem?
Is this a problem?
I won't tell
if you won't.
I never thought that
I would live to see the day.
I thought the one thing
that we could keep
our Riverdale safe from
was child predators.
Ms. Grundy's not a predator.
She's a good person.
Archie, you don't
have to defend me.
No, he doesn't.
Well,
they're not
denying it, are they?
They're clearly guilty.
I think the next step is
we take this
to Sheriff Keller,
and let the wheels
of justice take over.
Dad, you can't
let that happen.
- Son, it's complicated.
- She didn't force me
to do anything,
I went after her.
Everything that happened,
I wanted it to happen.
There's no surprise there.
Why are you
doing this, Mom?
Putting Ms. Grundy on trial?
This isn't just about her.
This is about him.
I want you see
what kind of person
Archie truly is.
Wait a minute, that is
what this is about?
Your crazy grudge
against my teenage son?
I'm never going to stop being
friends with Archie, Mom.
- Ever.
- We are done here.
- Oh, we are far
from being done here.
- Stop.
- Shut up.
- Stop!
Please.
You're right, Mrs. Cooper.
You're right. I'm selfish,
and I'm stupid, and
I don't deserve to be
your daughter's friend.
But please,
don't hurt Ms. Grundy
because you wanna hurt me.
This isn't about
hurting anyone, Archie.
It's about
doing what's right,
and, of course,
informing our neighbors.
Alice, I swear to God...
- You swear to God...
- Publish one word
about this, Mom,
and I will tell everyone that
I broke into Ms. Grundy's car.
- Betty...
- That I robbed her,
and made up
the story of their affair.
It will be like,
I finally...
Snapped.
Like Polly.
- Betty...
- It'll prove what everyone
already thinks about us.
"Crazy runs in that family."
Like mother, like daughter.
- You wouldn't dare.
- I'll quit.
I'll quit my job.
Will that satisfy you?
Yeah, it will. It has to.
And I absolutely
would dare, Mom.
She has to leave town.
- The hell she does.
- Son.
Why does she need
to leave town?
Because it's what's best.
And Alice will keep her word.
- I will.
- I'll pack up my things,
I'll be gone by morning.
Ms. Grundy.
How'd you like the movie?
Quite the twist ending.
Oh, my God.
- Veronica.
- What the hell was that?
I saw you with that biker guy,
that Serpent.
And don't tell me
you were just being polite.
I was handling some
unfinished business
for your father.
I'm gonna need
more than that, Mom.
Details,
specifics.
All right, then.
Your father hired
the Southside Serpents
to help decrease the value
of the drive-in's land
so he could purchase it
at a cheaper price
using an offshore LLC.
What you saw was
me paying them
for a job well done.
So...
Daddy's the anonymous buyer?
And he's doing this from jail?
He has an extremely
long reach, your father.
And he's sunk every last penny
that we have into this deal.
So...
Dad really is...
Dad is a businessman.
He saw an opportunity,
and he took it.
And it was happening anyway.
Old Riverdale's dying.
He's just simply
helping it along.
- But it's wrong.
- Wrong?
Well, did you like
living at the Dakota
with a Central Park view?
Did you like
your personal shopping
account at Barneys?
How about our family dinners
at Jean Georges?
Your Hermes?
- Those were
just things, Mom...
- That was our life, Ronnie,
provided to us
by your father.
Understand?
You are not
those things you said.
You're not stupid.
This wasn't your fault.
Betty.
Polly kept so,
so many secrets from us.
I won't have any more
secrets between us.
Not anymore.
Not if I'm gonna
keep you safe.
What's my name, Mom?
Say it.
- Elizabeth Cooper.
- That's right.
I am Elizabeth,
I am not Polly.
Archie is not Jason.
So stop using them
as an excuse
to control my life!
"Dear Diary, love
makes you do crazy things,
"and maybe some of what I did
was wrong, but maybe...
"Maybe I was right
about some things, too.
"Maybe Ms. Grundy
was dangerous in some way.
"Tomorrow morning,
when we wake up,
"the world will,
yet again, be changed."
They'll tear
that booth down, too.
Raze the whole place.
Send it to the junkyard.
And us with it.
Yeah...
Maybe they'll save it.
All the pieces.
Store it in
the town hall attic,
and rebuild it
in a hundred years.
Wonder who the hell we were.
Hmm.
So where are you
gonna live now?
I'll figure it out, Dad.
I always do.