♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(shout)
Skinner!
(gasps) Uh,
Superintendent Chalmers!
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just bought myself a car.
Oh. Oh, good.
This will sound crazy
but at first, I thought
I'd enraged you again.
-Skinner!
-What? What?
Ah, you're getting paranoid.
You know,
I used to think a car
was just a way of getting
from point "A" to point "B"
and on weekends, point "C,"
but that was the old me.
That man died the moment I laid eyes
on the 1979 Honda Accord.
I've always admired car owners,
and I hope to be one myself
as soon as I finish
paying off Mother.
She insists I pay
her retroactively
for the food
I ate as a child.
Yeah, yeah.
That's unfortunate.
Well, Seymour,
I make superintendent money
which amply covers
both food and car.
Holy jumping Caesar's catfish!
My "H" has been stolen.
Oh, that's how people
know it's a Honda.
What's the point
of having a Honda
if you can't show it off?
Sir, if you'll just
stop yelling at me
I'm sure I can
find a replacement.
(grunting)
Here we... I'll just...
Hey! Get away from my car!
-Uh-oh. This way.
-Uh-oh.
(register bell dings)
(chuckling)
(whistling)
Eh... morning, Apu.
Good morning.
One doughnut
with sprinkles...
(gasps) Wait a minute,
these are not sprinkles, sir.
-What do you mean?
-You've clearly taken items
from the candy rack and placed them
on top of the doughnut
in an attempt
to pass them off as sprinkles.
Well, it was like that
when I got here.
-It really was.
-A Mounds bar is not a sprinkle.
A Twizzler is not a sprinkle.
A Jolly Rancher
is not a sprinkle, sir.
Perhaps in Shangri-La
they are, but not here.
-(moans)
-(bell chimes)
APU:
Thank you. Come again.
(police radio chatter)
Ah, looks like
we put the kibosh
on another two-bit
telephone swindle, boys.
Frankly, I would have expected
better from Jimmy the Scumbag.
Meh.
-Hey, what's this thing?
-Huh? Well, that's an auto-dialer.
This bird was using it to
pull a telemarketing scam.
But instead, he's going
to rot in the slammer
for the next 20 years.
Bread and water,
icy showers,
guards whomping
your ass round the clock,
and the only way out
is suicide.
Telemarketing, eh?
(snickering)
Ha-ha!
(boys laughing)
Oh, you think
this stolen "H"
is a laugh riot,
don't you?
Well, I'll tell you
something that's not so funny.
Right now Superintendent
Chalmers is at home
crying like a little girl.
(loud laughter)
(chuckling)
I guess it is a little funny.
Nonetheless,
I will find the culprit.
We'll start with...
oh, I don't know...
Bart Simpson.
Um, I don't think you want
to look in there, sir.
Balderdash. I'll just
stick my head right in...
half a dozen eggs?
Well, that would be
the complete dozen.
All right, rather than tempt
fate, I'll move along now.
And so we reach
the bottom of the barrel,
Nelson Muntz.
(hums fanfare)
The cold, hard process
of elimination places the "H"
squarely in your locker.
(both gasp)
Ha-ha!
Damn! Dang! Darn!
(gasping) A principal's ransom
in stolen goods.
Well, sir,
who's ha-ha-ing now, hmm?
I don't know, but he's
got lethal tuna-breath.
ALL: Ooh!
Who does Nelson think
he's impressing anyway
acting so cool
all the time?
Not me.
All right, Mr. Smartenheimer,
that does it.
First, you're going to give back
everything you've stolen.
Then I'm sentencing you
to one week
of the lowest, most degrading
work known to man.
-Janitorial work.
-Ah, gee.
I'm standing right here, sir.
Ah, yes. Uh...
Take a good look
at him, Nelson,
'cause that's where
you're headed.
After you claim
your stolen merchandise,
go directly to Mr. Muntz
for an apology.
Bite me.
Cram it.
You're dead.
Get bent, ma'am.
Why do you have to be such
a pain all the time?
Don't you realize you're
getting a bad reputation?
Don't you realize
your butt sticks out?
It does not.
-Hey!
-Ha-ha!
An automatic dialer?
Is that legal?
I don't want you
getting arrested, Homer.
I won't.
Or swindling our neighbors.
Let me show you
how it works.
This baby has every phone number
in town programmed into it.
It automatically calls them
one by one and plays my message.
Listen.
(touch tones beeping)
(telephone ringing)
Ahoy-hoy?
HOMER:
Greetings, friend.
Do you wish to look
as happy as me?
Well, you've got the power
inside you right now,
so use it and send one
dollar to Happy Dude,
742 Evergreen Terrace,
Springfield.
Don't delay.
Eternal happiness
is just a dollar away.
Hmm...
one dollar
for eternal happiness.
Mmm...
I'd be happier
with the dollar.
(chuckling) Now we just sit
by the mailbox
and watch
the money roll in.
But you're going to annoy
thousands of people
just to make
a few measly dollars.
It's nothing but panhandling.
Tele-panhandling.
And should there be requests
for an encore,
we will reprise
"Pop Goes the Weasel."
Otherwise, we will
file out quietly.
-(sighs)
-(water splashing)
And that's how Willie waters.
Now, you take the hoose.
The moose?
The hoose! The hoose!
Is this right?
Agh, turn off the noozle!
The noodles? What noodles?
The noozle at the end
of the hoose.
(laughing)
Miss Simpson?
Do you find something funny
about the word tromboner?
No, sir. I was laughing
at something outside.
She was looking at Nelson.
ALL:
♪ Lisa likes Nelson ♪
She does not.
♪ Milhouse likes Lisa ♪
He does not.
♪ Janey likes Milhouse ♪
She does not!
♪ Uter likes Milhouse ♪
Nobody likes Milhouse.
Lisa, you've got detention.
(grumbling)
Oh, how does Bart
do this every week?
Hey, brainiac. Since when
do you get detention?
It's your fault. I accidentally laughed
at your immature prank.
Ha! Yeah.
The best part
was when he got wet.
Hey, you're doing that
the stupid way.
If you use that deal
with the five chalks
you'll get done faster.
Thanks, but I prefer
the honest way.
Whatever.
Smell you later.
Hmm.
Wow, that was
a good idea,
and I can't believe
it came from Nelson.
(thinking) He's not like anybody
I've ever met.
He's like a riddle
wrapped in an enigma
wrapped in a vest.
Sure is ugly, though.
So why can't I stop
staring at him?
Oh, no.
I think I'm getting a crush
on Nelson Muntz.
Hey, Willie!
Catch the football!
All right, I'll--
-(Willie screaming)
-(bees buzzing)
(dreamy sigh)
-(laughing)
-Milhouse, I've never told anyone
this kind of thing before,
but I've never felt
this way before.
-I think I have a crush...
-(gasps)
Uh, oh, really?
On Nelson Muntz.
(gagging)
Way to drink, Poindexter!
(coughing)
You like Nelson?
But he's a creep,
and he chipped
one of my permanent teeth.
But I bet underneath
he's a sweet, sensitive
person... like you.
I guess you could say
I want to bring out
the Milhouse in Nelson.
But I'm all Milhouse!
Plus, my mom says I'm the
handsomest guy in school.
I like you too, Milhouse,
but not in that way.
-You're more like a big sister.
-No, I'm not.
Why does everybody
keep saying that?
Would you do me a favor?
When you get back to class,
just give him this note.
Ohh...
Please?
(thinking) When she sees you'll do
anything she says,
she's bound to respect you.
Sure!
What's a big sister for?
Oh... I shouldn't
have said that.
"Guess who likes you."
(siren wailing)
Milhouse, I'm so sorry.
He can't hear you now.
We had to pack
his ears with gauze.
Nelson. Um...
that note Milhouse gave you,
it wasn't from him.
It was from... me.
You? Why would you like me?
No girls like me.
Are you wearing a wire?
I don't know why
I like you, I just do.
So... what do you think?
It's okay... I guess.
Do I have to do anything?
Well, would you like
to come over to my house
after school?
Okay.
But if anybody sees us,
I'm just there
to steal your bike.
(tires screeching)
(panting)
Huh? Ooh.
Whoo-hoo!
Two dollars!
It's working!
I don't feel any happier.
How about you?
Mmm, a little.
(wheels squeaking)
Oh, you got to see this.
It's so cute what she does.
Be the baby, kitty.
Go on. Be the baby!
(laughs)
Come on.
-(cat yowling)
-Snowball!
-(cat shrieking)
-You don't understand.
She loves to climb in here.
I believe you!
I don't care!
Hey, Lise, Mom said you had
the toenail clippers, and--
Whoa, Lisa! Look out!
Nelson's in our house!
It's okay.
I invited him over.
-Nelson's my new friend.
-Are you nuts?
I'll probably never
say this to you again,
but you can do better.
Please don't ruin
this for me, Bart.
I think he's starting
to like me.
-Milhouse likes you.
-Oh, please!
Milhouse likes Vaseline
on toast.
Hmm.
(dialing)
(whirring)
Oh, pawns can't move that way,
you stupid arm!
-(phone rings)
-Lab.
HOMER (on recording):
Greetings, friend.
Do you wish to
look as happy as me?
(gasps) Why, it's the
AT-5000 auto-dialer,
my very first patent.
Ah, would you listen
to the gibberish
they've got you saying?
It's sad and alarming.
You were designed
to alert schoolchildren
about snow days and such.
Well, let's get you home
to Frinky.
-Hope your wheels still work.
-(keypad beeping)
(vibrating, whirring)
Oh, no, you don't.
(grunts)
You're the first person
I've had over to the house
since my dad went nuts.
"Nuke the whales"?
You don't really
believe that, do you?
I don't know.
Gotta nuke something.
Touché.
You play the guitar?
Oh, yeah.
I'm a superstar.
Would you play a song for me?
Oh. Okay.
(strings tuning)
♪ Joy to the world ♪
♪ The teacher's dead ♪
♪ We barbecued her head ♪
♪ What happened to her body? ♪
♪ We flushed it down
the potty ♪
♪ And round and round
it goes ♪
it... goes ♪
I wish I could laugh
at the idea of a teacher
being decapitated.
I know.
(chuckles)
It's funny, huh?
Hardly.
Listen, I'm getting
pretty tired.
I'm going to go
to sleep for a while.
Smell you later.
-How am I supposed to get home?
-I don't know.
You should have thought of that
before you came over. Heh.
I feel so stupid, Mom.
Nelson's not right
for me at all,
and I don't think
he ever will be.
Well, most women will tell
you that you're a fool
to think you can change a man,
but those women are quitters.
-What?
-When I first met your father,
he was loud, crude,
and piggish,
but I worked hard on him,
and now he's a whole new person.
-Mom?
-He's a whole new person, Lisa.
Oh, I know.
Mmm.
I wonder if I could
change Nelson.
Very sharp.
Oh, but I feel
like such a tool.
I know it's a change,
but it highlights your sweet
and sensitive side.
Aw, crap.
LISA:
Isn't it nice up here?
What are you thinking,
Nelson?
What am I thinking about what?
-About anything.
-Nothing.
Mm... what do you feel?
What's inside you right now?
Guts and black stuff...
and about 50 Slim Jims.
Come on, Nelson,
you must think and feel things.
I mean, look where we are...
a rolling, green hillside,
the stars coming out
like God is lighting
a million tiny candles.
The moon looking down
on us as if to say...
(gasps)
My first kiss.
I always wondered
what it would be like.
This ought to shut her up.
Hey... this isn't so bad.
That was pretty fine.
See? You do have
a tender side.
You just needed someone
to bring it out.
Yeah. That was
pretty rockin'.
Oh, man!
You kissed a girl!
That is so gay!
Listen, you thugs!
Stop making fun of him or you'll be sorry.
ALL: Whoa!
You'll be so sorry
when you realize
how you've hurt the feelings
of a sweet young man.
(groaning)
He's not like you anymore.
He's changed.
And he doesn't want
to hang around
with a bunch of crumb-bums.
Crumb-bums?
Nobody calls me a crumb-bum.
Hey, back off, James.
I'll handle this, Lisa.
You go have a fig bar.
Hey, thanks for
embarrassing me, dingus.
You asked for it, man.
You're broadcasting
geek rays
over the entire valley.
'Fraid not.
I'm still wicked bad.
Oh, yeah?
Then prove it, ass butt.
Come raid Skinner's
house with us.
We found a bunch
of rancid coleslaw
in the Dumpster
behind Krusty Burger.
Yeah, and we're going
to go heave it at his house.
Cool!
I'd love to get even
with Skinner.
Uh...
Uh, but I better not.
(clucking)
Chicken!
-Lame-o!
-Girl lover!
-Fancy pants!
-Charlatan!
You got rid of them,
and you did it like a gentleman
without any violence.
Yeah.
I know you don't
like that stuff.
(touch tones beeping)
(phone ringing)
NED:
Howdily-diddely.
HOMER:
Greetings, friends.
Do you wish to look as--
Oh, it was that
darn recording again.
Of course it was.
It's been calling all night.
Just unplug the phone.
-(phone ringing)
-Howdily...
-Greetings, friends.
-Dang!
I told you to unplug the phone.
-But it could be my mother.
-(ringing)
-Howdy--
-Greetings, friends.
-Shoot!
-That is it, Ned.
If you don't unplug
that phone right now,
you're sleeping on the lawn.
Will you two shut up?
People are trying to sleep!
(loud thumping)
Great Barrier Reef!
We're under attack!
Eat slaw, Skinner!
We're slawing him
up good!
Nelson doesn't know
what he's missing.
Why is he wasting his time
with that Simpson chick?
'Cause your mom had
a three-month waiting list.
-All right!
-I knew you'd be back.
Hey, what'd you say
about my mom?
(all talking at once)
I missed you guys.
Let's never fight again.
Who's out there? Give me your names
so I can tell the police.
AGNES: Seymour,
what's going on?
What's that odor?
Go back to bed, Mother.
I've got it under control.
Listen, you crumb-bums.
If you think I'm impressed,
I am not. (stammers)
Oh, brandishing your buttocks
is only getting me angrier.
AGNES: I want to see
what's going on!
No, Mother,
don't look out the window!
-(Mother screaming)
-(sighs)
-(siren wailing)
-Cops! Everybody split up.
-(thuds)
-Lisa, the cops are chasing me.
I need a place to hide.
Lisa's window is the next one.
(phone ringing)
-NED: Howdly-doo...
-Greetings, friends.
MAUDE: Ned, did you plug
that phone back in?
Shut up!
And I wasn't
even there, honest.
Skinner's just out to get me.
-That's so unfair.
-(siren approaching)
Uh-oh.
Meet me at the back door.
Aha! I had a feeling
we'd find you here.
-Chief, no!
-What'd you do that for?
Well, that thing's been
driving the whole town nuts.
Got me out of the bath
seven times. Seven!
Hey, who shot the auto-dialer?
Marge's auto-dialer.
See you in court, Simpson.
Oh, and, uh, bring
that evidence with you.
Otherwise, I got no case
and you'll go scot-free, you know.
Uh, Chief, what about
those coleslaw punks?
Well, I can't be everywhere
at once, Lou, now can I?
You know, in most cities,
the chief of police
doesn't even go out
on calls like these.
-Yeah, yeah. We know, Chief.
-We appreciate it.
-Count our blessings every day.
-We're very appreciative.
I think they're giving up.
Thanks for helping me out.
You're a stand-up babe.
Hey, check it out.
Skinner's mopping the goo
off his house.
Wait till he finds
what I left in his birdbath.
SKINNER: No!
I thought you weren't there.
Huh?
Oh, yeah.
Uh... I guess I was.
-You lied to me.
-Nuh-uh.
There. You did it again.
All right, all right, I lied.
I'm sorry. Let's kiss.
No! You don't understand,
Nelson.
A kiss doesn't mean anything
if it's dishonest.
Um... there's
a niceness to it.
I was foolish to think
I'd actually changed you.
Maybe I was
seeing things in you
that weren't really there.
Definitely.
Then why did you want
to be with me?
Mmm-mm, maybe 'cause you
were the first person
that ever thought there
was a nice guy inside me.
Hmm. Well, guess you really
blew that one, huh?
Well, I guess this is it.
You mean, like, good-bye?
Let's just call it
"smell you later."
(sniffing)
Hi, Lisa.
Could I talk to you,
or would that just make
Nelson whale on me again?
Don't worry. Nelson and I don't
like each other anymore.
(gasps)
Really?
You got anybody in mind
for your next crush?
Well, I'm really not
thinking about that now.
I suppose it could be
almost anybody.
Yes!
(touch tones beeping)
(phone ringing)
Hello. This is Homer Simpson,
A.K.A. Happy Dude.
The court has ordered me
to call every person in town
to apologize for
my telemarketing scam.
I'm sorry.
If you can find it
in your heart to forgive me,
send one dollar
to Sorry Dude,
742 Evergreen Terrace,
Springfield.
-You have the power.
-(machine clicks)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.