♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(static)
(chomping noisily)
(plate squeaks)
Marge, can't we
get some clear plates?
I can't see the TV.
Is it really necessary
to watch TV while we're eating?
We're getting food all over.
Yoink!
If you really wanted us
to be neater
you'd serve us
out of one long bowl.
You're talking
about a trough.
We're not going
to eat from a trough.
And another thing,
it's only 5:15.
Why are you
in your underwear?
Hey, this ain't
the Ritz.
At least let's have a civilized
conversation, shall we?
Lisa, how was school?
How was what?
What?
School! School!
It's not time
for school.
I know it's not--
(groans)
I'm going into
the dining room
to have a conversation.
Anyone who wants
to join me is welcome.
MARGE: Hello, Marge,
how's the family?
I don't want
to talk about it.
Mind your own business.
Keep it down in there,
everybody.
Homer, is this the way
you pictured married life?
Yeah, pretty much.
Except we drove around in
a van solving mysteries.
Well, I pictured
cocktail parties
and candlelit dinners.
I pictured napkins!
Homer, I want to throw
a dinner party.
Oh, I hate
having parties.
The toilet
always gets backed up.
I don't care
if the sink shoots sludge.
We're having a party.
Man, that is flagrant
false advertising!
It's just not a dinner party
without a melon baller
and we'll need a citrus zester
a ravioli crimper.
Ooh, an oyster mallet.
"Made in U.S.A."
Oh, no, thank you.
Hey, Lis,
check this out.
Nonstick coating.
Ooh.
A punchbowl like that
just screams good taste.
Wouldn't it be perfect
for the dinner party?
Oh, we can't afford that.
Who do you think
I am, Liz Taylor?
Well, maybe we could
use it once
and then return it.
Marge, we're not
talking
about a toothbrush here.
Bart, company's coming.
Go put doilies under the coasters.
Hurry! Hurry!
(bell rings)
Lisa, quick,
screw these back on.
Mom, calm down.
The party's not for
another three hours.
Oh, good.
That will give me time
to add another coat
of glaze to the ham.
(grunts)
Homer!
HOMER:
What?!
Are you ready?!
Just got to put my shoes on.
The only thing I asked
you to do for this party
was put on clothes
and you didn't do it.
(doorbell rings)
And now it's too late!
They're here!
Bart, greet our guests
and take their coats.
Mom, Reverend Lovejoy
doesn't have a coat.
Should I let him in?
My coat was stolen
at last week's
interfaith banquet
so I helped myself
to a few
of the better umbrellas.
Well, as you can see
we don't believe
fur is murder.
But paying for
it sure is.
(laughing)
Uh, sorry we're late
but Luann had to
put on her face.
She doesn't want
anyone to know
she's got no eyebrows.
What? You don't.
(all conversing)
Did anyone see that
new Woodsy Allen movie?
You know, I'd like
his films except for
that nervous fellow
who's always in them.
If you want to talk nervous,
you should have seen Kirk deal
with the high school boys
who egged our Bonneville.
I should've asked them
to hurl some bacon.
Then maybe I could've had
a decent breakfast for once.
HOMER: You know what
you two need?
A little comic strip
called "Love Is".
It's about two naked eight-year-olds
who are married.
Hmm, well...
Marge, if that was
my last meal
I'd tell the warden, "Bring on
the lethal injection".
Yeah, Marge, I know
I haven't eaten that well
since I was in the army.
Or that noisily.
All right, that's it.
So, who wants
to play a game?
Hmm, hmm, hmm?
Oh... That's a
noodle scratcher.
(gasps):
Cornstarch!
Oh, righty-oh!
It's good for keeping
down the urges.
Oh, come on, Luann.
You know what this is.
Kirk, I don't know
what it is.
Ah, it could not be
more simple, Luann.
Do you want me to show
this to the cat
and have the cat
tell you what it is?
'Cause the cat's
going to get it.
I'm sorry I'm not
as smart as you, Kirk.
We didn't all
go to Gudger college.
It's "Dignity!" Gahh!
Don't you even know
dignity when you see it?
Kirk, you're spitting.
Okay, genius,
why don't you draw dignity?
-(all exclaiming)
-Oh, that's dignity all right.
Worthy of Webster's.
It's no wonder
I can't draw dignity.
I gave it up
when I married her.
Now, Kirk,
it's only a game.
Sometimes, we--
Aw, cram it, churchy!
Maybe we should all have
a few drinks.
I'd have a drink,
but it might
loosen my tongue.
You want to talk?
Go ahead, Luann, talk.
Why don't you
tell them
one of your little
bedtime stories, huh?
Like the one about
how rotten it is
to be married
to a loser.
Or how about
the one about
how I carry a change purse?
Yeah, a purse!
Shut up and let the woman talk.
Okay, Kirk,
I'll tell a story.
It's about a man
whose father-in-law
gave him a sweet job as
manager of a cracker factory.
HOMER:
Boring.
A man whose complete lack
of business sense
and managerial impotence...
Ooh, here we go.
...sent the number-one
cracker factory in town
into a tie for sixth with
Tabletime and Allied Biscuit.
KIRK: You want to hear
a secret, everybody?
Luann loves it--
Loves it--
When I fail.
Oh, yes, Kirk, I love having to
borrow money from my sister.
I love having to steal clothes
from the church donation box.
Oh, sweet Jesus.
Lisa, why don't you
come sing for us?
♪ You're a grand old flag... ♪
Oh, great.
You got the kid singing.
I hope you're happy now.
I am not happy
and I haven't been happy
for a long time.
I want a divorce!
(all gasping)
A... divorce?
Sure. Divorce.
Hey, you got it,
toots
and here's a picture
even you can figure out.
It's a door! Use it!
That's a door?
Hello, I'm Doctor Hibbert.
I'm afraid I'm going to have
to amputate your butt.
(all laughing)
All right,
if you think you must.
Come on, Milhouse,
we are going.
Aw, can't I come home later?
There's not going to be
a home later.
Oh, okay.
Ta-ta, I'm off
to the beauty salon.
Good night.
Thanks for coming.
We'll see you.
Bye-bye.
Well, I think that
went pretty well.
(tires squealing)
What?
I feel terrible.
The Van Houtens
split up at our party.
Marge, please.
That was 20 minutes ago.
I shouldn't have served
those North Korean
fortune cookies.
They were so insulting:
"You are a coward."
No one likes to hear that
after a nice meal.
You can't keep
blaming yourself.
Just blame yourself
once and move on.
You know who the real
victim is in all of this--
Milhouse.
Hey, Van Houten,
I heard your folks broke up.
Aren't you going
to say, "Ha-ha"?
Oh, by no means.
My dad left my mom
after she got hooked
on cough drops.
By the end,
her breath was so fresh...
she wasn't really
my mother anymore.
Oh.
So I guess
I'm not alone.
Ah, you'll do fine.
My divorce was tough on my kid
but he got over it.
I sleep in a drawer.
♪ I dig the nightlife ♪
♪ Got the boogie... ♪
(humming)
I must say, Luann,
you're really
handling this
splendidly.
From now on, forget everything
you thought you knew
about Luann Van Houten.
Actually, Luann,
I don't really
know anything
about you.
Forget it.
She's gone.
Presto-chango!
Kaboom!
Sweet Fanny Adams!
Bye-bye!
Singles life
is great, homer.
I can do whatever I want.
Today I drank a beer
in the bathroom.
The one down the hall.
Yeah. And another great thing:
you get your own bed.
I sleep in a racing car.
Do you?
I sleep in a big bed
with my wife.
Oh. Yeah.
(knocking)
Hey, there, Kirk.
Oh, boy, what's going on?
Patio party?
No. A possum drowned
in the pool.
You have any garbage bags?
Uh, just throw it
over the fence.
Let Arby's worry about it.
That's Jerry.
He's a major player
down at the sewing store.
Well, thanks
for introducing me.
Oh, don't worry, Homer.
You know me
and I'm a superstar
at the cracker factory.
KIRK: You're letting me go?!
Kirk, crackers
are a family food.
Happy families.
Maybe single people
eat crackers; we don't know.
Frankly, we don't
want to know.
It's a market
we could do without.
So that's it--
After 20 years
so long, good luck?
I don't recall
saying good luck.
(imitating car engine)
And the winner
of the Milhouse 500 is...
Milhouse!
LUANN:
Milhouse, are you sure
you want
to drive that inside?
Yes.
Okay. Be careful,
sweet, sweet treasure.
(doorbell rings)
God, I missed you, Lu-Lu.
(giggles)
Chase...
It's only been three hours.
Who's Chase?
Oh. That's mom's
new boyfriend.
Hey, I know you
from American Gladiators.
You're Pyro!
Only on weekends.
During the week
I'm just your average
work-a-day stuntman.
Really?
Go ahead.
Break a chair on me.
(grunts)
Wow! Thanks.
Okay, boys,
I got to go.
Come on, Lu-Lu,
let's roll.
(whistling)
(yelling)
Ow! Gee. Ow!
What the hell
is wrong with you?!
Geez, sor-ry.
It's a pretty standard
stunt, Homer.
MARGE:
Homer, get ready!
For what?
Remember?
Luann and Chase
are taking us out
to hear Spalding Gray.
I don't want to go to that.
You said you'd do it
as a favor to me.
That doesn't sound
like something I'd say.
Fine. I'll go
without you.
Okay. Love ya.
Homer, I want you to meet
my new special lady.
Say hello to Starla.
(cigarette sizzling)
Can I have the keys
to the car, lover?
I feel like
changing wigs.
Okay.
Starla's a temp
at K-ZOG radio 530.
She's going to help me
launch my singing career.
(engine racing
and tires screeching)
My car!
Oh, my demo tape!
"Can I Borrow a Feeling?"
(laughing)
That's your picture
on the front.
Go ahead, Homer,
laugh at me.
I already did.
(sighs)
You know why
all this happened, don't you?
'Cause I took
my marriage for granted.
You know, in 12 years
I never once helped out
with the housework?
Oh, yeah,
you got to do that.
I could've at least
stayed in shape for her.
Oh, and for yourself.
I could've taken
just a little time
to make her feel special.
It can't just be sex.
It can't.
God, I was so self-centered.
No wonder
I didn't see it coming.
That's how it is, though.
One day your wife is
making you your favorite meal
the next day
you're thawing a hot dog
in a gas station sink.
Oh, that's tough, pal.
But it's never going
to happen to me.
Well, how do you know?
What makes you guys so special?
'Cause Marge and I
have one thing
that can never be broken:
A strong marriage built on
a solid foundation of routine.
Marge, I'm home.
Where are you?
Are you okay?
I don't smell dinner.
"Dear Homer..."
Aw.
"Sorry you didn't want
to join me tonight.
"I left you hot dogs
for dinner.
They're thawing in the sink."
(screams)
Hi, Dad.
You know, there's
buns in the cabinet.
Lisa, wait.
I know you're only
eight years old
and I don't want to put
a lot of pressure on you
but you've got
to save my marriage.
Oh. Okay.
Can I stay up?
Mmm... all right.
(clearing throat)
As you know,
there's been
a lot of talk
about divorce lately
and I think your mom
might not be happy with me.
You've done a lot of crazy stuff
over the years
and she stood by you.
Why would she
leave you now?
'Cause there's lots of stuff
she doesn't know about.
You mean, like your poker shack
out in the swamp?
Mm-hmm.
She knows.
Oh, I knew this would happen.
Our whole marriage started off
on the wrong foot.
MAN:
Dearly beloved, we are gathered
in the sight of God
and this casino to join...
Homer.
-And...
-Marge.
In holy matrimony.
By the power vested in me
by the state gaming commission
I pronounce you
man and wife.
Here's ten dollars
worth of chips.
You may kiss the bride.
Mm...
See?
You don't have to spend
a lot of money
to have a first-class
wedding reception.
(Marge sighing)
It's getting less
and less likely
you're going
to yell "Surprise"
and have all my
friends jump out.
"Levi's."
Hey, you think that truck
is full of jeans?
You're very lucky
to have mom.
That's your advice?
Go to bed.
Good morning.
You know, Marge,
I was thinking
about how much I enjoy
your interests
so I wandered over
to that theater
you went to last night
and I bought tickets
to their entire season.
Look, Mostly Madrigal.
Hey, that might be good.
Oh, oh, An Evening
with Philip Glass.
Just an evening?
Voices of
the Elderly Poor. Hmm...
Homey, I appreciate this
but I'd really like
to get some sleep.
Oh, of course, my sweet.
I'll just make some
soothing ocean sounds for you.
(blowing)
(imitates fog horn)
(squawking)
(inhales)
Arr, matey.
(humming)
Armando, don't you think
you're taking a lot off--
(screams)
Homer, what are you doing?
I wanted to surprise you
with a kicky summer do.
How many husbands would
do that for their wives?
None-- They'd have
more sense than that.
Ooh... you're feisty.
I'm going to give
you a Madonna cut.
Mmm! Homer
I don't need you around me
24 hours a day.
I'm a grown woman.
I can take care of myself.
Now will you please
just go away?
Oh... I just
made things worse.
A few clumsy gestures
aren't going to make up
for ten years of neglect.
Marge deserves someone
who will treat her right.
Marge deserves a fresh start.
I'd like to file for...
divorce.
These things happen.
Eight dollars.
Only three cavities, Bart.
Your best checkup ever.
I'm going to make
you my specialty--
Butterscotch chicken.
HOMER:
Marge?
Can you
come in here?
We need to talk.
ALL: Surprise!
(gasping)
Surprise.
Marge, will you
marry me?
Why, am I pregnant?
No.
It's a second wedding, honey.
Our first one was so crummy,
I had to make it up to you.
I really love you.
Oh, Homey.
I know you love me.
We don't need
to get married again.
Yes, we do.
I got us a divorce
this afternoon.
What?!
I didn't want
a hokey second wedding
like those ones on TV.
This one is for real.
I want our marriage
to be perfect
right from the start
so we don't end up
like Kirk and Luann.
We never will.
Dearly beloved--
Wait.
I want one last chance
to enjoy single life.
(belches)
Okay, ready.
I will now
read these special vows
which Homer has prepared
for this occasion.
"Do you, Marge, take Homer
in richness and in poorness,"
"Poorness" is underlined--
"In impotence and in potence
"In quiet solitude
"Or blasting across
the Alkali Flats
in a jet-powered,
monkey-navigated..."
And it goes on like this.
It doesn't matter.
All I want to know is
will you make me the luckiest guy
in the world...
again?
I will.
Oh, Homey,
of course I will.
Come on, you stupid...
(grunts)
By the power vested in me
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
It's the most
perfect wedding
I could ever ask for.
You've even got a hip
rock 'n' roll combo.
Okay, everybody,
who likes the Doobie Brothers?
'Cause we've got one of them.
♪♪ (soft jazz music)
What a wonderful evening.
A magical way for two people
to renew their love.
Marge is right.
I-I've got something
I'd like to say.
Would you guys do a favor
for a guy in love?
-Sure.
-Yeah.
That's why
we're here.
KIRK:
Hi, everybody.
Hi.
And hit it!
♪♪ (upbeat romantic
pop playing)
♪ Can I borrow a feeling? ♪
♪ Could you lend me
a jar of love? ♪
♪ Hurtin' hearts
need some healing ♪
♪ Take my hand with
your glove of love ♪
♪♪ (romantic pop playing)
How about it, Luann?
Will you marry me... again?
Ooh, no.
Ohh...
Well...
Uh, can I have my
shirts back, at least?
Okay, you heard the lady.
Why don't you take
it outside, all right?
Uh, I'll be back.
KIRK:
Prob-probably.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.