♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Ahh!
-(tires screech)
D'oh!
(snoring)
(sucking)
(distressed moaning)
(muttering):
I want lemonade.
Hmm, pressure dropping,
humidity rising
over 80%, increasing wind?
Here we are, chapter two:
"So Your Pressure
Is Dropping?"
(gasps)
Dad, wake up!
What is it? Wha..?
I think a hurricane is coming!
Oh, Lisa.
There's no record of a hurricane
ever hitting Springfield.
Yes, but the records
only go back to 1978
when the Hall of Records
was mysteriously blown away.
(whining)
What is it, boy?
Fire? Earthquake? Hippies?
-(yelps)
-Hurricane!
Somehow the animals are
always the first to know.
KENT BROCKMAN: And the weather
service has warned us to brace ourselves
for the onslaught
of Hurricane Barbara.
And if you think naming
a destructive storm
after a woman is sexist,
you obviously
have never seen the gals
grabbing for items
at a clearance sale.
Hmm. That's true,
but he shouldn't say it.
We better pick up
some supplies.
Stand behind the
flaming garbage cans.
We'll be letting you
into the store
70 people at a time.
Oh let's just beat him up
and take his stuff!
No, no, no!
Do not listen to that man.
Remain calm.
You will all have a chance
to be gouged.
-(appreciative murmurs)
-MARGE: Thank goodness.
-(clamoring)
-Whoa.
Oh, there's so little left.
Mom, let's just grab what we can
and get out of here.
This storm
is making people crazy.
The last pineapple...
And plenty ripe too!
But I'm not fruit!
I'm a kid!
That's what the pumpkin said.
Hi, Lisa.
We're going
to be in a pie!
Sir,
for your own safety,
we do advise you
to evacuate.
I ain't leaving!
I was born
in this nursing home,
and I'll die
in this nursing home!
Is there any chance
of you changing your mind?
Sure. Let's go.
Well,
need some help there?
You know, maybe you folks
should come over
and hunker in our bunker.
Oh, it'll be fun.
We're going to go through our
old canceled checks and receipts
and give ourselves
an audit--
Make sure we don't owe
anything extra.
Oh, I'm sure
I'd be a third wheel.
(chuckles)
No, siree. We'd be happy
as hens to have you--
I would make it my business
to be a third wheel.
Okely-dokely.
Ooh, I better go take down
the manger scene.
If baby Jesus got loose
he could really
do some damage.
Okay, it's the standard
Grampa drill.
Everybody
into the cellar!
♪ The Hurricane ♪
Awesome!
So long, suckers!
ALL:
Aww!
(crackling)
ALL:
Yay!
(wind howling)
Why don't we do something
to take our minds
off the storm?
Ooh, a Rubik's cube!
Let's all work it together.
Okay, start
with diagonal colors...
HOMER: Use your main finger
on the yellow side
and your other finger
on the orange side
and turn it.
My main finger?
-Orange to orange!
-You've got to start backwards!
(all yelling)
One at a time!
Spin the middle side
top-wise.
-Top-wise!
-Now I remember why I put this down here
-in the first place!
-(clatters)
(electricity crackling)
(thunder rumbling)
(harmonicas playing)
It's dying down!
-All clear, everyone.
-Dad, no!
This may just be the eye
of the hurricane.
Relax. Can't you see
how eerily calm it is?
See? I told you it was over.
Hmm... I don't remember
a bowling alley being there--
(screams)
Dear God,
this is Marge Simpson.
If you stop this hurricane
and save our family,
we will be forever grateful
and recommend you
to all our friends.
So if you could find it
in your infinite wisdom to--
Wait.
Listen, everybody.
(birds chirping)
The hurricane's over.
He fell for it!
Way to go, Marge!
Remarkable!
There doesn't seem to be
any damage at all.
It just goes
to show you
that everything
will work out
if you have faith.
-(wood clatters)
-(sighing)
It's all gone.
Everything...
Gone-diddily-on.
Maude?
Rod?
Todd?
I'm right here, Daddy.
Oh, Neddy,
it was terrifying.
I thought I was headed
for the eternal
bliss of paradise.
Oh, my gosh!
Look at Rod!
I have a headache.
Well, sir,
everyone's alive.
Guess that's something
to be thankful for.
Now, that kind
of attitude's
not going to get
your house back.
I'm sure your insurance
will cover the house.
Uh, well, no.
Neddy doesn't
believe in insurance.
He considers it
a form of gambling.
You know,
it's kind of funny.
The only thing
that survived the storm
were the family
tombstones.
They're all
we have left.
Well, call us
if you need anything.
We got new clothes
from the donation bin!
I'm a surfer!
Look, Daddy,
Todd is stupid
and I'm with him.
And now Mommy's stupid.
(laughs)
Looking good, Rod.
Looking good.
(sighs)
Neddy, I know this has
been a terrible day
but, by golly,
first thing tomorrow,
we're going to open up
The Leftorium,
and before you know it,
we'll be back on our feet.
Down here at Springfield mall
a storm-addled crowd appears
to have turned its rage
on The Leftorium.
(glass smashing)
Surprisingly, people are
grabbing things with both hands,
suggesting it's not just southpaws
in this rampaging mob.
(moaning)
Try looking in the back.
Meantime, Springfield bowlers
will be happy to hear
that the Bowl-a-Rama is
back in business at its new location
teetering over
the Carter-Dixon tunnel.
(bowling balls striking)
(people cheering)
Reverend Lovejoy?
With all that's happened
to us today, uh...
I kind of feel like Job.
Well...
Aren't you being
a tad melodramatic, Ned?
Also, I believe Job
was right-handed.
But, Reverend,
I need to know.
Is God punishing me?
Ooh... Short answer:
"Yes" with an "If."
Long answer:
"No" with a "But."
Uh, if you need additional
solace, by the way,
I've got a copy
of something or other
by Art Linkletter
in my office.
Even in my darkest hour,
I can turn
to the good book for...
Son of a gun-diddily-un!
Those gilded edges smart.
Why me, Lord?
Where have I gone wrong?
I've always been nice to people.
I don't drink or dance or swear.
I've even kept kosher
just to be on the safe side.
I've done everything
the Bible says--
Even the stuff that contradicts
the other stuff.
What more could I do?
I--I feel like
I'm coming apart here.
I want to yell out,
but I--I just can't
dang-diddily-do-dang-do-don-
diddily-darn do it.
I--I--I...
(sighs)
Ned! Maude!
You've got to go back
to your house!
Something incredible
has happened!
Oh, what happened now?
Did the rubble burn down?
No! Come on!
CROWD:
Yay!
(gasps)
Oh, they rebuilt
our house.
Oh! It's a miracle.
I started making some calls last night,
and before I knew it,
practically all of Springfield
was offering to help.
-Mm-hmm. My pleasure.
-Happy to help.
-Fabulous experience.
-Sure!
Hope you like it,
neighbor.
We didn't have the best tools
or all the know-how,
but we did have
a wheelbarrow full of love.
And a cement mixer
full of hope
and some cement.
Oh, it's wonderful.
I--I--I... I don't know
how I can possibly repay you
but if any of you
ever need a favor
just look for the happiest man
in Springfield.
No, no, not me, friends.
He's talking about himself,
but thanks for looking.
(cheering)
The living room
and dining rooms
with a lovely flow
for entertaining...
-Uh-huh.
-(shirt rips)
And-- Oh!
Looks like a loose nail.
Eh, one out of 25
ain't bad.
Your beautiful
kitchen, Ned.
Just as you
remember it.
Was that, uh...
Was that toilet always
next to the refrigerator?
Uh, Ned,
you ever try lugging a toilet
up a flight of stairs?
Lisa and I built
your room.
But I don't like this clown.
Uh, I wouldn't
take it down
if I were you.
It's a load-bearing
poster.
(ceiling cracking)
(electricity buzzing)
Now, this is a room
with electricity
but it has
too much electricity.
So I don't know.
You might want
to wear a hat.
Uh-huh.
The floor feels
a little gritty here.
Yeah. We ran out
of floorboards there
so we painted the dirt.
Pretty clever!
Oh! Something is definitely
wrong with this hallway!
Come on in!
It's your master bedroom!
Ow! My nose!
Well, I've seen about enough.
So, Flanders,
what do you think
of the house that love built?
Aw, shoot!
(sighs)
(huffing)
(lens cracks)
Aww...
Now calm down, Neddily-diddily-
diddily-diddily-diddily.
They did their best,
shoddily-iddily-iddily-diddily.
Got to be nice--
Hostility-ilitity-bility-dility.
Aw, hell,
diddily-ding-dong crap!
Can't your morons
do anything right?!
-(crowd gasping)
-Hey!
Ned, we meant well,
and everyone here
tried their best.
Well, my family and I
can't live in good
intentions, Marge!
Oh, your family
is out of control
but we can't blame you
because you have
good intentions.
Hey, back off, man!
Oh, okay, dude.
I wouldn't want you
to have a cow, man.
Here's a catchphrase
you better learn
for your adult years.
Hey, buddy,
got a quarter?
(all gasping and murmuring)
I am shocked and appalled.
Mr. Flanders,
with all due respect
Bart didn't do anything.
(gasps) Do I hear the sound
of butting in?
It's got to be
little Lisa Simpson,
Springfield's answer
to a question no one asked!
-(goofy laughing)
-What do we have here?
The long, flabby arm
of the law?
The last case
you got to the bottom of
was a case of Mallomars!
Mallomars.
Oh, that's going in the act.
Oh, yeah, the clown,
the only one
of you buffoons
who doesn't
make me laugh.
And as for you,
I don't know you,
but I'm sure
you're a jerk!
Hey, I've only been here
a few minutes.
What's going on?
You ugly,
hate-filled man.
Hey, hey, I may be ugly
and hate-filled, but I, um...
What was the third thing
you said?
Homer...
you are the worst human being
I have ever met.
Hey, I got off pretty easy.
(crowd murmuring)
Neddy? Uh, wait.
Where you going?
(tires squealing)
♪ Aloha oe... ♪
♪ Doo-doo-doo-doo ♪
♪ Mamboo-looboo-boom-boo ♪
♪ Nee-dee-dee... dee ♪
I just attacked all my friends
and neighbors
just for trying to help me.
I'd like
to commit myself.
Very well.
Shall I show you to your room,
or would you prefer
to be dragged off
kicking and screaming?
Ooh, kicking and screaming,
please.
As you wish.
(screaming)
Flanders?
Ned Flanders?
I'd better call Dr. Foster.
(ringing)
Yes, Dr. Foster here.
Ned Flanders?
You're sure?
No, no, no,
I'll come right over.
And may God have mercy
on us all.
Darling, there's an emergency
at the hospital.
Where are my shoes?
Oh, I think
they're in the den.
In the den?
May God have mercy
on us all.
Well, how are you feeling
this evening?
Uh...
actually,
I'm a little chilly.
Can I have another straitjacket?
Of course.
Thank you.
Dr. Foster!
Hmm... Well, at least
your memory is not crazy.
Now, Ned,
you may remember
we spent some time
together 30 years ago.
Do you recall what you
were like back then?
-Oh, sure. I was a good little boy.
-Were you?
Whee! I'm Dick Tracy!
Bam! Take that, Prune-Face!
Now I'm Prune-Face.
Take that, Dick Tracy!
Now I'm Prune Tracy.
Take that, Dick...
Ned, stop it at once!
-Stop it!
-(film flapping)
I can't believe
I was such a terror.
Well, neither
could your parents.
That's why they brought you
to me.
Well, I'm afraid young Ned
is unusually aggressive
but I can't seem
to find a cause for it.
Hey, hey!
Get down
from that bookshelf, please.
Most of those books
haven't been discredited yet.
Would you please
tell your son to stop?
We can't do it, man.
That's discipline.
That's like
telling Gene Krupa
not to go boom, boom,
bap-bap-bap, boom, boom!
(imitating drumming)
Boom! Boom! Tiss!
Hmm... Lack of discipline.
I'm beginning
to see the problem.
We don't believe in rules.
Like, we gave them up
when we starting living
like freaky beatniks.
You don't believe in rules,
yet you want to control Ned's anger.
Yeah. You've got
to help us, doc.
We've tried nothing,
and we're all out of ideas.
Hmm... There is
an experimental therapy
that might help Ned
contain his anger.
It was known as
the "University of Minnesota
Spankalogical Protocol."
And that's just
about eight months...
Hmm... Now.
Well, Ned,
how do you feel?
I feel...
Fine.
You don't feel...
Angry?
Abso-tively not-arino.
How do you feel about me?
Pretty darn
diddily-doodly...
good.
The only problem
with the treatment
was that it worked too well.
You became unable
to express any anger at all.
From that point on,
any time you felt angry
you could only respond
with a string
of nonsensical jabbering.
Well, I'll be
darn-diddily-arned.
Yeah, that's the stuff.
You suppressed your rage
for so long
it finally erupted as
a massive public explosion.
It sure did-diddily-id.
All right, all right,
just watch it there.
I'm here to help,
you know.
Now, I'd like
to try something.
Is there any person
who makes you
particularly angry?
(phone rings)
Yello?
Yes?
Mental hospital?!
I don't know
any Ned Flanders.
The man who lived
next door
until his house
blew down.
Oh, him.
Mr. Simpson?
Dr. Foster.
Please come with me.
You folks are free
to roam the grounds.
Just remember:
One of our patients
is a cannibal.
Try to guess which one.
I think you'll be
pleasantly surprised.
MAN: Everyone outside
of this room is against me!
I can hear you walking by--
It stinks! It stinks!
It stinks!
Yes, Mr. Sherman,
everything stinks.
We want to teach Ned
to release his anger
in healthy doses.
We need someone
so irritating
that Ned simply will not be able
to repress his rage.
Homer,
can you be that annoying?
(grunts)
What?
Get in the booth.
"Ned Flanders,
I mock your value system.
You also appear foolish
in the eyes of others."
(chuckles)
Well, howdy, Homer.
Ooh, thanks
for dropping by.
Mm, he's not
responding.
Proceed to level two
antagonism.
"Past instances in which
I professed to like you
were fraudulent."
Oh, well, I'll just
have to try harder.
(chuckles)
Ooh! Thanks for dropping by.
Ah, he's still repressing.
Maximum hostility factor.
"I engaged in intercourse
with your spouse
or significant other."
Now, that's psychiatry.
Huh? Huh?
(forced laugh)
Very funny, wise guy.
Aw, that's it.
You just can't
insult this guy.
You call him a moron
and he just sits there
grinning moron-ally.
Hi, neighbor.
You know what your problem is,
Flanders?
You're afraid
to be human.
(chuckles) No.
Now, why would I be afraid of that?
Because humans are
obnoxious sometimes.
Humans hate things.
Well, maybe a few
of them do...
Back east.
I can't find what
Homer's saying.
Did you write that?
Um... Did you like it?
Come on, Flanders.
There's got to be
something you hate.
What about mosquito bites?
Mmm-mmm.
Sure are fun to scratch.
Mmm, satisfying.
What about, uh...
fluorescent lights?
Oh, they hum like angels.
You're never lonely if you've
got a fluorescent light.
See?
You like everything.
No, that's not true.
I--I--I... I don't like
the service at the post office.
You know, it's all rush, rush,
get you in, get you out.
Then they've got those
machines in the lobby--
They're even faster.
No help there.
You might even say...
I hate the post office.
That and my parents.
Lousy beatniks.
Hey, that felt good.
He just said
he hates his parents.
Do you know
what that means?
Uh, what do you think?
It means he's cured.
That's what I said.
(cheering)
Thanks, everyone.
I'm all better now.
No more storing up the anger
till I explode.
If any of you does something
I don't like,
you are going to hear
about it.
(cheering and applauding
and whistling)
Yes, that's
very healthy, Ned.
And if you really tick me off,
I'm going to run you down
with my car.
-Ha!
-Yeah... Um...
(scattered applause)
(chuckles)
Ned, you so crazy.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.