♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
D'oh!
(screams)
ANNOUNCER: Ladies
and gentlemen,
the Springfield Mall
in conjunction with
Nostalgia Licensing
Corporation
is proud to present...
the stars of "Bonanza"!
♪♪ ("Bonanza" theme)
Thank you. I just
wish Ben and Hoss
and Little Joe
and Hop Sing and Sheriff Roy
and all of your favorites
could be alive today
to see
this wonderful turnout.
You know, on the series
we were always trying
to kill the Cartwrights.
(crowd booing)
But it looks like
father time
took care of that
for us, right?
Am I right, folks?
♪♪ ("Bonanza" theme)
Oh, this sucks.
Weren't there three Indians
last year?
Look, Marge!
They opened a new
high-tech gadget store!
-You love high-tech gadgets.
-No, I don't.
Like bull, you don't.
Come on.
Homer, please!
You're hurting my arm!
(laughs)
No, I'm not!
Hey, Lis.
Check out this
space-age toothbrush.
That's an electric
nostril groomer.
(coughs)
Night vision goggles?
A bathroom scale
from a Soviet sub?
A suede briefcase case?
Mm. Anyone who needs
this kind of status symbol
must have some terrible
emotional problems.
(gasps)
Marge, look!
"The world's best jacket."
if I had this,
it would show everybody!
(growling maniacally)
Show everybody!
Yes, finally!
I would like to return
your "ultimate belt."
I see. Do you have
a "receipt," sir?
No, I do not have
a receipt.
I won it as a door prize
at the Star Trek convention
although I find their choice
of prize highly illogical
as the average Trekker
has no use for
a medium-sized belt.
Whoa, whoa! A fat,
sarcastic "Star Trek" fan.
You must be a devil
with the ladies.
Hey, I-- that-- Oh...
Gee, I hate to let
you down, Casanova,
but no receipt,
no return.
I'll give you
four bucks for it.
(sighs)
Very well.
I must hurry back
to my comic book store
where I dispense the insults
rather than absorb them.
Wow! I bet if God
wore pants
he'd have a belt
like that!
This isn't a belt.
It's a tactical
pants-retaining system.
Check it out:
Compass, matches,
whistle, saw,
panic button, squirrel snare,
radon/lie detector,
sphygmomanometer,
and it's even got
turn signals.
(all exclaiming)
Hey, Simpson.
Want to trade belts?
Well, not really
'cause yours is just
a piece of extension cord.
Hey, dude, he's ragging
on your cord.
Get him.
No running.
Time for a little
evasive action.
Hey!
He's turning left!
Help! Help! Help!
Help! Help!
I was hoping
it wouldn't come to this
but you guys asked for it.
Can't you read?!
Call the police!
Hey, Dad.
Looking good, son.
Hey! What happened
to your belt?
Some bullies beat me up
and took it.
Son, there's only one thing
punks like that understand--
squealing.
You've got to squeal
to every teacher
and every grown-up
you can find.
Coming to me
was a good start.
But then they'll just
beat me up even worse!
Yes. They are a clever bunch.
I know. I'll squeal for you--
to their parents.
(grunting)
JIMBO'S FATHER: That's for telling me
how to raise my lousy kid.
And this is for
the crummy life
I've had to live.
The thing is--
(grunts)
Bart really loves
that belt, and--
Hey, something's wrong
with this guy.
He's not falling down!
-(shotgun cocking)
-MOE: Fun's over, fellas.
If you're gonna beat up
my friend in my bar
there's a
two-drink minimum.
Geez, Homer,
I never seen
a guy stand up to that
kind of punishment.
I mean, you took
a three-man pounding
and didn't even fall down.
Big deal. I didn't even
get my kid's belt back.
The only thing a loser
like me is good for
is taking beatings.
There you go!
That's the spirit!
Homer, I've seen
prizefighters
couldn't take a punch
half as good as you.
You know, boxing might be
right up your alley.
-Really?
-Oh, please!
It's
the good life, Homer.
Some of these boxers
they eat steak and
lobster and salad bar
all in a single meal.
(gasps)
Dressing?
Their choice.
You really think
I could do it?
Well, I don't know.
Are you man enough to test
every one of your limits?
-Yes.
-And are you man enough
to throw a punch,
should the opportunity arise?
-Yes!
-And are you
man enough to give me
a 60% cut?
-Yes!
-I'll take it.
Woo-hoo!
MOE: Now Homer,
if I'm going to manage
your boxing career,
I want you to have
complete faith in me.
Here, let me show you something.
Wow, I've never
been in here before.
Yeah, well, when I realized
we hadn't had no ladies in here
since 1979
I turned it into an office.
You used to be a boxer
just like me?
Yep. They called me
"Kid Gorgeous."
Later on, it was
"Kid Presentable."
Then "Kid Gruesome,"
and finally, "Kid Moe."
Hey, what's this?
Aw, that's my old
spit bucket.
Yeah, I've been meaning
to empty that out.
(gasps)
You know Lucius Sweet?!
He's one of
the biggest names in boxing.
He's exactly as rich
and as famous
as Don King and he looks
just like him too.
Yeah, he was my manager.
Back when I was gorgeous,
everybody wanted a piece of me,
but somehow I just never made it
to the big time.
Why not?
'Cause I got knocked out
40 times in a row.
That plus politics.
You know, it's all politics.
Lousy Democrats.
(Marge growling)
Homer, of all
the crazy ideas you've had
this one ranks
somewhere in the middle.
You're 38 years old.
You don't know how to box
and you haven't gotten
any exercise since grade school.
Before you even consider this,
I insist you consult a doctor.
No problemo.
A competent doctor!
HOMER: D'oh!
Well, sir, you more than meet
every one of this state's
requirements
to box, wrestle
or be shot out of a cannon.
(growling)
That's what we get
for living in a state
founded by circus freaks.
You have an absolutely unique
genetic condition
known as
"Homer Simpson syndrome."
Oh, why me?!
Don't worry,
it's quite beneficial.
Your brain is cushioned
by a layer of fluid
one-eighth of an inch thicker
than normal.
It's almost as if you're wearing
a football helmet
inside your head.
Why, I could wallop you all day
with this surgical 2x4
without ever knocking you down,
but I have other appointments.
All right, Homer
let's see the left.
(grunts)
O-kay.
Let's see the right.
(panting)
Just a second.
When you're ready.
All right.
I'm ready.
Wait a minute.
All right.
Just a second.
Okay, punching isn't your thing,
but that's okay.
You're not that kind
of fighter.
What you're going to do
is stand there
while your opponent gets
exhausted from overpunching.
Then I can just push him over.
That's right, and if the ref's
not looking
you can kick him
a couple of times.
-Who's gonna knock you down?
-No one.
-When are you gonna fight back?
-Never!
-What are you gonna do?
-Nothing!
That's my boy!
Man, you'd never get me
into a ring.
Boxing causes brain damage.
Okay, you're fighting
a guy named Boxcar Bob.
Brawled his way up
from the boxcars, did he?
No, not yet.
He still lives
at the train yard
but he's a hungry
young fighter.
In fact, he's actually
fighting for a sandwich.
Homer, I want you to
have my lucky mitts.
I hope you do better
with them than I did.
Gee, thanks, Moe.
What's this?
Ah, that's the barbed wire.
We called that
"the stinger."
They don't let you
use that no more.
Now, no matter
how much he hits you,
you don't do
nothing, okay?
You don't want
to get drawn
into a boxing
match here.
(bell rings)
Way to go, Dad!
Take those punches!
Man, that tramp's
got the energy of a hobo.
Yeah, he never
stops punching
except to check
out his bindle.
Okay, Homer, he's tired.
He's tired.
Now's your chance.
Nudge him, nudge him.
(cheering)
♪♪
Hello, Moe.
Delightful to see you again.
Lucius! Hey, what's a glitterati
like you doing in my dump?
I thought you were managing
the champ.
Yes, managing Drederick
has been my highest priority
even though he is
temporarily incarcerated
for pushing his mother
down the stairs,
but with his
impending release
I've been strategizing
for his glorious return
to the shores of fistiana.
Uh... what?
His comeback fight.
You know-- boxing?
Oh, man. Yeah.
Well, who's donating his body
for that one, huh?
Well, word is you manage
a stalwart young pugilist
who cannot be knocked down.
Homer?
You want Homer to fight Tatum?
Well, the fans are weary
of fights that are over
before they have
an opportunity
to even get drunk.
I just need a body
who can sustain
verticality
for three rounds.
Yeah, but Homer's no boxer.
He's just a freak.
Tatum will fustigate him.
Well, fustigation aside, Moe,
you've got a choice.
You can either sit here
in the ladies' room
with your faded memories,
or you can take your last shot
at the big time
and I can make it happen.
(jingling)
Three rounds.
That's all I ask.
I got to be honest
with you, Homer.
I didn't bring you up here
to show you my new tar paper.
You didn't?
No. Homer,
how would you like
to be heavyweight champion
of the world?
-Oh, sure.
-Great.
All you got to do
is fight Drederick Tatum.
It's this Saturday.
Here's your parking pass.
Ooh. "General."
Who's Drederick Tatum,
anyway?
-Is he another hobo?
-Uh... you know what?
I'm gonna have to
check on that.
Well, I trust you, Moe.
If you say I can
beat this guy
then he doesn't
stand a chance.
(alarm wailing)
(shouting)
Hey, guys, come on.
Shut up.
(silence)
We didn't know
you were here.
-Sorry, champ.
-It was Jerry.
MAN 1:
Champ, champ.
Do you feel remorse
for your crime?
Oh, yes.
Believe me, my God,
if I could turn back the clock
on my mother's stair pushing,
I would certainly reconsider it.
MAN 2: Drederick, what do you think
of Homer Simpson?
I think he's a good man,
I like him.
I got nothing against him,
but I'm definitely gonna
make orphans of his children.
MAN 3: You know,
they do have a mother, champ.
Yes, but I would imagine
that she would die of grief.
(reporters shouting)
Thank you, thank you
but the champ has no time
for further queries.
This parole hearing
is over.
(reporters groaning)
I wanted to know what it was
like in prison.
Homer,
why are they saying
you're going to fight
Drederick Tatum?
(gulps)
Uh... well...
I was gonna
surprise you, but...
happy anniversary, baby!
Have you lost your mind?!
Oh, come on!
I'll make a fortune
for one night's work.
We can have all the things
we always dreamed of--
a snooty butler,
carpeted carports,
those blue cupcakes
they sell sometimes--
But you'll get killed.
Marge, will you
let me finish?
Plug-in room
deodorizers,
front and rear spoilers
for the car.
Mom's right, Dad.
The odds against you winning
are a thousand to one.
I don't think
it's that unlikely.
Those are the odds
they're giving in Vegas.
All right
I think we've heard
just about enough
from Mr. Newspaper today.
MAN: Society put
Drederick Tatum away
for his brutal crime,
but he's paid his debt,
and now he's going
to get revenge
on Homer Simpson.
BOTH: Yay!
That's your daddy.
T-shirts. Get your T-shirts.
Tell them where you've been
by wearing a T-shirt.
BART:
You'll be okay, Dad.
Just make sure he hits you
an even number of times
so you don't end up
with amnesia.
Moe, I'm so glad
I found you.
Please, promise me
you won't let Homer get hurt.
Hey, I'm not the
villain here, okay?
If Homer gets killed
in the ring tonight,
it will be because of
your negative attitude.
-There, I said it.
-Listen to me!
The instant that Homer's
in any kind of danger,
I want you to
throw in this towel
and stop the fight!
All right, all right,
all right, I promise, okay?
Thank you.
Celebrities at ringside tonight:
star of the "McBain"
action films
and feature player in the
Hollywood prostitution scandal,
Rainier Wolfcastle!
TV anchorman and
Springfield institution,
Mr. Kent Brockman!
(crowd booing)
This just in:
Go to hell.
From the world
of organized crime,
say hello to
Anthony "Fat Tony" D'Amico!
And the ruiner
of events worldwide--
title fights, the Super Bowl
and the Nixon funeral--
ladies and gentlemen,
the Fan Man.
Ah, cripes.
Now I've got to comb
this side over.
All right, Homer,
I'm not gonna lie to you--
there's a good chance
you can beat Tatum
but you've got to visualize
how you're gonna win, okay?
Gotcha.
(crowd cheering)
A congenital heart defect
has apparently felled Tatum
moments before he could
step into the ring.
And now, please welcome back
into decent society,
ladies and gentlemen,
the heavyweight champion
of the world,
Drederick Tatum!
(cheering)
♪♪ (rap)
Let's get ready to rumble!
♪ In this corner we have
the full-body snatcher ♪
♪ P-funkadelic
and I gotcha ♪
♪ Hard enough that I could
chew a whole bag of rock ♪
♪ Chew an avenue
chew an off street ♪
ANNOUNCER: And to challenge
the irresistible force
of Tatum
we have the immovable object.
He's been called
"the brick hithouse"
and is also known as
"the southern dandy,"
Homer Simpson!
♪ Why can't we be friends? ♪
Your boy looks
a little soft, Moe.
You do remember
our arrangement?
Yeah, don't worry.
You'll get your
three rounds.
Stupendous.
Because if he goes down
before that bell rings,
your future's going with him.
Okey-doke. Future
down the crapper. Gotcha.
Due to popular demand,
we will forgo
our national anthem.
And now, ladies and gentlemen
l-l-l-let's get ready
to rumb-l-l-le!
-(cheering)
-(bell dings)
Okay, Homer, nothing
to be worried about. Just--
(crowd gasps)
Wow! I've never seen Dad
hit somebody like that before.
What are you
talking about?
Isn't Dad the one
in the black trunks?
-No.
-Uh-oh.
What, what,
what am I missing? What?
ANNOUNCER: And there's Tatum
showboating for the crowd.
Geez, only six seconds in.
Attaboy, Homer.
Keep dancing.
ANNOUNCER: Showing utter disdain for
his opponent's abilities,
Tatum is taking a short,
midround breather
to converse with actor
Charlie Sheen.
You know what's great there
is the sea bass.
They do it blackened or sauteed.
It's stupendous.
Okay, break it up,
break it up, you two.
MARGE: Homer!
Homer, he's not going
to get tired.
You've got
to hit him back.
Hit him back!
HOMER:
That cactus is right.
I've only got one chance.
I've got to knock him out.
D-o-h-h-h-h!
Hang in there, Homer.
Only 440 more seconds.
He's getting
his second wind.
No. He's getting killed.
He's gonna die
on his feet.
I can't watch this.
I've got to get out of here.
Fight!
Somebody stop the fight!
Where's the doctor?!
Kill him! Kill him!
ANNOUNCER:
It looks like it's all over.
Tatum wants to finish this
with one punch,
and here it comes.
(heart beating slowly)
ANNOUNCER: Oh, my God!
Simpson's manager
has flown into the ring
and is airlifting him out.
Ladies and gentlemen,
whatever dignity
remained in boxing
is literally flying out
the window.
Are you an angel?
Yes, Homer, I'm an angel.
All us angels
wear Farah slacks.
But you stopped the fight.
Won't everyone
be mad at you?
Let them be mad.
The only thing
that matters to me
is you're safe.
D'oh!
Sorry.
Homer, your manager
obviously loves
you very much.
Lucius, would you
do that for me?
Absolutely, I would.
Now get in the van.
You couldn't even give me
one lousy round, Moe.
You will always
be a loser.
Now take your check
for $100,000
and get out
of my sight.
I don't need
your stinking money.
Oh, Homie, are you okay?
I can't remember
where we parked.
That's all right.
We'll just wait till
everyone else leaves.
I got your tooth, Dad.
Uh, not mine.
Thank you, Moe.
I know you gave up
your dreams for Homer.
Well, what do dreams
matter, Marge?
I was able to stick up
for a pal.
Well, so long, Springfield.
Where are you going?
Nowheres in particular.
I just need some time to think.
Hey, there you are!
You give me
that contraption back!
♪ People who need people ♪
♪ Are the luckiest people ♪
♪ In the world ♪
♪ With one person ♪
♪ One very special person ♪
♪ They're
the luckiest people ♪
♪ In the world ♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.