♪ The Simpsons ♪
D'oh!
(screams)
♪ They fight and fight ♪
♪ They fight and fight
and fight ♪
BOTH:
Dad! V-chip! V-chip!
Sorry, sorry. My fault.
♪ ...Scratchy show! ♪
(sniffling)
(gasps)
ANNOUNCER: We interrupt this cartoon
for a special report.
Someone found my keys.
Kent Brockman
at the action news desk.
A massive tanker has
run aground
on the central coastline
spilling millions of gallons
of oil on Baby Seal Beach.
Oh, no!
It will be okay, honey.
There's lots more oil
where that came from.
Preliminary reports
indicated
the ship's captain
was drunk at the helm.
Those reports
were later confirmed.
Arr. I'm in a lot
of trouble now...
Hey, I'll give you
a hundred bucks
to take the blame.
A clean-up effort
is already underway
and as always,
the first to pitch in
are those unsung heroes
Hollywood movie stars.
(barking)
This isn't about publicity.
This is about
cleaning off gunk.
As a golden globe nominee,
I just think it's our duty
to make the real globe
a little more golden.
LISA: We'd be doing our part
for the environment.
Plus, we'd get to clean up
all those cute animals.
Honey, we don't need
to drive 400 miles
to clean animals.
You can stay right here
and give the dog a bath
or trim the cat's nails.
Oh, Mom, please.
You can make
this my birthday
and Christmas presents.
You've already used up your
birthday and Christmas presents
on that peach tree
we got you
and you hardly ever play
with that anymore.
Yes, I do.
Sure, I do. Look.
♪ Here I am playing on
my peach tree, Mom ♪
Oh, all right,
we'll go.
Now, the cat needs
his medication every morning.
No problem.
Can do.
The furnace has been giving off
a lot of carbon monoxide...
-Gotcha.
-So keep the window open.
Cat in the furnace.
Uh, you know,
I think I'll take
Maggie with us.
And if anything happens,
just use your best judgm--
Mmm...
Just do what I would do.
BOTH: Woo-hoo!
A whole week of just
father and son.
See you at dinner.
(both whistling)
What time?
You know...
I don't know.
Shall we say 10:00?
All right,
just wake me up.
(crunching)
You know,
Bart, I saw this one.
(mumbling)
ANNOUNCER: Live,
from the grand ballroom
of the Hapsburg
imperial palace
it's the world series
of bumper cars.
More food.
BART: Dad, do I have
to brush my teeth?
HOMER: No.
But at least rinse
your mouth out with soda.
(pop-top opening)
(gargling)
I'm going to rescue
a baby seal
and then I'm going
to save an otter.
Whoa, whoa, I'm sorry,
but all the animals
have already been
reserved for celebrities.
There. That's 104 pounds
of sandpipers.
You mean there's
nothing left to clean?
Well, there are rocks.
Thousands and thousands
of rocks.
I've got rocks
that need washing at home.
Geez, look at this place.
We got to do something.
Hmm, garbage angels?
(both laughing)
Dad, I think I need
some fresh air.
Can I go to the park?
Do I have
to sit up?
No.
Knock yourself out.
(engine buzzing)
Milhouse,
this is boring.
Make it crash
or something.
Perfectly level flying
is the supreme challenge
of the scale-model pilot.
-Give me that.
-Hey!
(engine buzzing)
(gasps)
Ah! It's gaining on us!
I'm pedaling backwards.
Abandon ship!
I don't like being
outdoors, Smithers.
For one thing, there are
too many fat children.
(gasps)
(engine sputtering)
Thanks a lot.
Now it's stuck
on that haunted house.
I heard a witch
lives there.
I heard a Frankenstein
You guys are way off.
It's a secret lab where they
take the brains out of zombies
and put them in the heads
of other zombies
to create a race
of super-zombies.
That's the house?!
(blows raspberry)
Stand aside, wussies.
(bell rings)
WOMAN:
Go away.
No children.
Enough talk.
(humming fanfare)
S-u-c-c-e-e-s, that's the way
you spell succ--
(screaming)
(gasping)
(laughing)
No, no.
H-help, h-help.
I'm gonna die.
(screams)
(groaning)
Oh, no!
The witch has Bart!
We've got to hurry.
(all screaming)
(doorbell rings)
HOMER:
Just a minute.
(paper tearing)
Hello?
Your son was trespassing
on my property
and destroyed a very valuable
stone gargoyle and--
Are you wearing a grocery bag?
I have misplaced
my pants.
I'm not going
to press charges
but I assume you'll
wanna punish him.
(laughing) Yeah,
appreciate the suggestion,
lady, but he hates that.
And I got to live with him.
You're the man, Homer.
Well, if you won't
discipline him,
I'll come back and
speak with his mother.
No, wait, wait.
Madam, I run a house
of discipline.
The boy will be disciplined
and disciplined severely.
Good day.
Oh, I don't know how
to punish you.
What does Marge
usually do?
She makes me taste beer.
Come on, boy.
Give your old man
a little credit.
Yeah, well, I still
get to punish you.
Now, you're going to do
chores for that lady
until you work off
the damage you did.
It's called
responsibility.
(crunching)
(screams)
(tires squealing)
(doorbell rings)
Come on in, Bart.
I can't believe
I've got to spend
all my free time
dusting doilies in a smelly,
run-down dump
for a creepy old witch.
♪♪ (cancan)
Lady, I got to tell you--
I have been grossly
misinformed
about witches.
Wow, man, what
is this place?
I prefer not
to be called "Man."
My name is Belle
and this is
the Maison Derriere.
That means the, uh,
"Back house."
Are you having a party
or something?
Nonstop.
We're a burlesque house--
A private club where gentlemen
can play some cards
and see a show.
Miss Belle,
we're about to do our
"Around the World" number,
but Monte Carlo
can't find her dice.
Here you go, darlin'.
Normally, we don't allow
children in here
but your father
was so insistent.
He's tough but fair.
I'll start sorting these bras.
That's a bit advanced
for you.
But I know
a stopped-up sink
that needs
some attention.
Just glad to be on the team.
BELLE:
When you work the door
the main things are
to greet the visitors
and toss out
the troublemakers.
Oh, the ol' greet 'n' toss.
No problemo.
How did I ever get along
without you?
(whistling)
Oop.
Is your name Bart?
-Mm-hmm.
-What the--
Does your father know
you're working here?
It was his idea.
In that case
I'll have a whiskey sour.
Oh, there's something
unsatisfying
about scrubbing
these rocks
and I think I know
what it is.
Lisa, I know
it's frustrating
but we made a commitment
and we have to see it through
no matter how unpleasant.
Quitting time. Okay.
Scrub up and head
for the communal tarp.
We're having
kelpburgers
and we're going to watch
a tape of Johnny Arvik.
He's the eskimo comedian.
Faster, Mom, faster.
Oh, that was
our emcee, Mel Zetz.
He got out of bed too fast
and broke his hip.
So who's going to warm up
the crowd tonight?
Well, whoever fits
Mel's tuxedo.
Eep!
The jokes are in
the breast pocket.
If you get in trouble,
there's a switch
that makes the bow tie spin.
"Heh, nudist colonies
are everywhere these days.
"I'd love to go, but I--
I can't get the wrinkles
out of my birthday suit."
(raucous laughter)
"But I got to tell you,
"Adam and Eve must have been
the first bookkeepers.
They invented
the loose leaf system."
(raucous laughter)
(chuckling)
If there's
a bad bookkeeping joke
I haven't heard it.
ANNOUNCER:
It's 11:00.
Do you know
where your children are?
I told you
last night, no!
Where is Bart anyway?
His dinner's getting
all cold and eaten.
Bart, where are you?
Come on!
I have to be up at 6:00 a.m.
to swipe Flanders' newspaper.
What the--
"President Eisenhower
celebrates
"40th wedding anniversary.
Not pictured, Mrs. Eisenhower."
I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
Bart was filling in--
I don't care if he
was filling for Mel Zetz.
He's my son and I don't
want him working...
so... late... that...
Oh, I agree.
Kids need rules
and boundaries.
Yes, everyone
loves rules.
It's so tough to be
a parent these days
what with all the gangs
and the drugs...
Oh, yeah, drugs.
You gotta have drugs.
Hey, he didn't pay the cover.
Oh, Bart,
he's your father.
We'll comp him
tonight.
Start a tab
tomorrow.
Oh, I hope I didn't miss
the floor show.
-Nope.
-Is Roxanne back?
Yup.
Did she, uh,
get my flowers?
-She did.
-I--
Hello, Bart.
Hello,
Principal Skinner.
This is the National Air
and Space Museum, isn't it?
(doorbell rings)
Uh, this isn't going to be
about Jesus, is it?
All things
are about Jesus, Homer.
Except this.
Your son has been working
in a burlesque house.
Principal Skinner
saw him with his own eyes.
That's true,
but I was only in there
to get directions on how
to get away from there.
Helen,
as a responsible parent
I was already
well aware of that.
Homer, I'm as permissive
as the next parent.
I mean, just yesterday
I let Todd buy some red hots
with a cartoon
devil on the box
but you can't possibly
think it's appropriate
for your ten-year-old son
to work in
a burlesque house.
Oh, no?
Well, if Homer Simpson
wants his ten-year-old son
working in a burlesque house,
then Homer Simpson's
ten-year-old son
is going to work
in a burlesque house!
That...
(nervous laugh)
Hi.
Now, Marge, you're gonna hear
a lot of crazy talk
about Bart working
in a burlesque house...
"Maison Derriere"?
I can't believe
there's a place
like that in our
wholesome little town.
Homer, did you know it
was a burlesque house
when you sent Bart
to work there?
No. I only learned that
four days ago.
What were you thinking sending
Bart to such an awful place?
I was trying to punish him
exactly like you would.
So, in a way
you really dropped
the ball on this one.
This is your mess
and I'll be damned
if I'm gonna clean it up.
(grumbles)
Please come in,
Mrs. Simpson.
How can I be of service?
I have a favor to ask.
Please shut
this place down
and move away
from Springfield.
Oh, honey,
you can't be serious.
Springfield doesn't
want places like this.
I think I know what
Springfield wants, sugar.
Oh? I've lived in this town
for 37 years.
I've lived here 52 years.
-I'm third generation.
-Sixth.
Get out of my town!
Listen, darling, we're just
as much a part of Springfield
as the church, the library
or the crazy house,
so I think I'll stay
right here... neighbor.
Is that so?
Well, sleazy entertainment
and raunchy jokes
will never be as popular
as sobriety and self-denial.
You're about to learn
the two most
dangerous words
in the English language
are "Marge Simpson."
It's the light
pink '87 wagon.
And after visiting
the area for, uh,
the past two months
I have determined it is
not feasible to construct
a super-train between
Springfield and Aruba.
(dejected groaning)
Next on the agenda is, uh...
The Citizens' Committee
on Moral Hygiene.
(dejected groaning)
I'm here to share
my moral outrage
but this time it's not about
that giant inflatable
Dos Equis bottle.
It's about a certain house
in our town.
What's wrong with this house?
Is it the plumbing?
No. It's a house of ill fame,
a house of loose ethics.
Is there a building code
violation?
A drainage issue?
A surveying error?
The house is perfectly fine.
Well, then quit bad-mouthing
the house.
Yeah. Leave
the house alone.
Oh, geez, it's what's inside
the house that's disgraceful--
Drinking, gambling
and debauchery.
It's right under our noses--
A secret house
of burlesque.
(gasping)
-Oh, my.
-MARGE: That's right.
KARL: That's not good.
People, this is an issue
that we as a town
are strong enough to ignore.
Let us give no more scrutiny
to this bawdy house
and its small clientele
of loyal perverts.
Oh, I'm afraid
this problem
goes far beyond
Eugene and Rusty.
(quiet murmuring)
Marge, if you please.
Julius!
Clancy!
CHALMERS:
Skinner?
-Seymour!
-Mother...
SELMA:
Patty?
WOMAN:
Cletus!
Oh. Uh, Barney.
Clancy!
Hey, come on!
You did me twice!
Smithers?
My parents insisted
I give it a try, sir.
HELEN LOVEJOY:
Mayor Quimby!
Uh, well, that could be
any mayor.
I rest my case.
Er, uh, well...
In light of these new facts,
of which I now realize
I was largely aware,
I must take action.
All in favor of demolishing
our beloved burlesque house
raise your hands.
(Marge clears throat)
Are they talking
about the bordello?
No, the burlesque house,
so just keep your mouth shut.
(mob grumbling)
Oh, there's no justice
like angry-mob justice.
I'm going to burn
all the historic memorabilias.
I'm going to take
me home a toilet.
Well, there'd
better be two.
(doorbell rings)
BELLE:
Who is it?
Uh, it's an angry mob,
ma'am.
Could you step outside
for a twinkle
while we knock down
your house?
Just a minute.
Stand aside, you degenerate,
two-bit proprietress.
Don't you call me that.
I'm an entrepreneuse.
Oh, shut up. You're wasting
valuable smashing time.
(yelling)
(glass shattering)
Dad, we can't let
this happen to Belle.
Do something.
Don't you worry, son.
My friends!
Stop!
Please hurry.
Sure. We could tear
this house down--
-(yelling)
-Yeah! Oh, yeah!
No! My friends, stop!
Let me finish.
We could tear it down
but we'd be tearing down
a part of ourselves.
♪ You could
close down Moe's ♪
♪ Or the Kwik-E-Mart ♪
♪ And nobody would care ♪
♪ But the heart and soul
of Springfield's in ♪
♪ Our Maison Derriere... ♪
♪♪ (jazz rhythm)
♪ We're the sauce
on your steak ♪
♪ We're the cheese
in your cake ♪
♪ We put the "Spring"
in Springfield ♪
♪ We're the lace
on the nightgown ♪
♪ The point
after touchdown ♪
♪ Yes, we put the "Spring"
in Springfield ♪
♪ We're that little
extra spice ♪
♪ That makes existence
extra nice ♪
♪ A giddy little thrill
at a reasonable price ♪
♪ Our only
major quarrel's ♪
♪ With your total
lack of morals ♪
♪ Our skimpy costumes
ain't so bad ♪
♪ They seem
to entertain your dad ♪
♪ The gin in your martini ♪
♪ The clams
on your linguine ♪
♪ Yes, we keep the... ♪
(boing)
♪ In Springfield ♪
♪ We remember
our first visit ♪
♪ The service
was exquisite ♪
♪ Why, Joseph
I had no idea ♪
♪ Come on, now,
you were working here ♪
♪ Without it
we'd have had no fun ♪
♪ Since March of 1961 ♪
♪ To shut them down now
would be twisted ♪
♪ We just heard
this place existed... ♪
♪ We're the highlights
in your hairdo ♪
♪ The extra arms
on Vishnu ♪
♪ So don't take the... ♪
(boing)
♪ We won't take the... ♪
(penny whistle)
♪ Yes, let's keep the... ♪
♪ ...in Springfield ♪
(horn honking)
(belching)
Well, I'm convinced.
The house stays.
This house is a very,
very, very fine house.
Here I come, everybody!
ALL: No! No!
Stop! Stop!
What are you
doing, Marge?
Didn't you
hear the song?
No. I had to go rent
the bulldozer.
Well, we all
changed our minds.
Yeah. Now we
love the house.
What about the sleaze
and the depravity?
It was a very
convincing song, Marge.
Mm-hmm. There were
kicks and everything.
Hmm... Can you sing it again?
I'm sorry.
It really was one of those
spur-of-the-moment-type things.
Well, I also have
a song to sing.
Don't make up your mind
until you hear both songs.
(clearing throat)
(coughing)
♪ Morals and ethics ♪
♪ And carnal
forbearance... ♪
(crashing)
(crowd gasping)
Uh... sorry.
Thanks a lot, Marge.
That was our only
burlesque house.
I do love it
when you drop by, Marge.
Next time, why don't we
get together at your house.
I'm so sorry.
How can we ever
make this up to you?
Oh, there's a way, Mom.
So, Twiggy, I hear you
and your husband Woody
just had a baby.
What did you name him?
Chip.
(drum sting)
Take it off!
All right, Dad, you've
been warned. Let's go.
Hey...
-Come on.
-Easy.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.