(faint heartbeat)
What is this?
Excuse me. Can somebody please tell me
what's going on here?
- We're collecting material.
- For?
For anything that might be
pertinent to the manhunt.
What manhunt? Manhunt for who?
You're kidding, right?
There's nothing. If you're looking for Mulder,
you're wasting your time.
- Are you listening?
- I'm not the man to talk to.
Whose stupid idea is this?
Somebody might have had
the courtesy to tell me.
There are agents in Mulder's office
who say they're part of an FBI manhunt.
I know. Believe me, this is not my idea.
I just found out about it myself.
They won't find Mulder this way.
We both know that.
I told you last night I will find him.
I'm gonna do that.
OK? I want you to cool out. I don't want you
doing anything to upset your pregnancy.
I don't understand. You are the assistant
director. Who's going over your head on this?
Our brand-new deputy director.
(phone rings)
AD Skinner, Agent Scully.
Thanks for getting right over.
I don't wanna lose any time.
One of our own is missing.
The only acceptable outcome
is that we find him, safe and alive.
- I'm sure the two of you agree.
- That goes without saying, sir.
Good.
This comes at a stressful time...
with my new appointment.
Thank you for your cooperation
in the hunt for Mulder.
Our cooperation?
With due respect, there aren't two people
better qualified to be directing this action.
You and AD Skinner are the two primary
witnesses to Mulder's disappearance.
I want your statement taken ASAP.
You make us out to be suspects, sir.
- Taken by who?
- My task force leader on this.
Special Agent John Doggett.
He's waiting to hear from you now.
One more thing.
Anything leaves this building
about aliens, or alien abductions,
or any nonsense that might cast
the Bureau in a ridiculous light,
and you can forget about
looking for Agent Mulder.
You'll both be looking for new jobs.
That's all.
I don't believe this.
This isn't about Mulder.
Kersh is covering the FBl's ass.
Why do I get the feeling they'd be happy
if we never found him at all?
Look... I saw what I saw. I have to make
a statement. I can't say it didn't happen.
You heard Kersh. They don't want the truth.
You give them it and they'll hang you with it.
They can hang me with a lie too.
I'm not gonna sell Mulder out.
What good are you to Mulder
if you give them the power
to ruin your career?
We Will find him.
Assistant Director, you can come with me.
Agent Scully, please wait on the wall
until we call you.
Water?
It could be a wait.
Thank you.
Aren't you his partner? Mulder?
Yes.
I guess nobody's
beyond suspicion on this thing.
Why are they talking to you?
Me? I knew Mulder back a bit.
They're developing a working profile,
character background.
I'd say they have
all the character profile they need.
Certainly his reputation.
I doubt we agents ever truly
know each other, even our partners.
Not at the end of the day.
Their real lives, their friends, girlfriends,
deeply personal things, issues.
- I think I know Mulder as much as anybody.
- Yeah, probably so.
I always took the rumours with a grain of salt.
- What rumours were those?
- Well, you know.
That from the beginning he never felt a real
trust with you, that you were ambitious.
Where'd that come from?
There are women here at the Bureau
that he would confide in.
I don't know if you knew that or not.
No.
- When was this?
- I don't know, it's just talk.
So what do you think happened... to Mulder?
What's your theory?
What's my theory?
My theory is you don't know Mulder at all.
You never did.
John Doggett.
Kersh's task force leader.
You might have just introduced yourself.
I was gettin' around to it.
Nice to meet you, Agent Doggett.
(vom its)
(dialling phone)
Hi, this is Margaret Scully.
Please leave a message.
Mom, it's Dana. I'm sorry
I haven't called you in a while.
I've been busy with work
and with something... else that I should
probably tell you about in person.
I don't even know if you're in town
or if you're checking your messages.
But, um...
But I really need to see you and talk to you.
There's a lot of stuff that's going on with me
right now, and I just really need to talk.
(crackling)
Mom?
- John Doggett.
- Stay out of my business!
Who is this?
- You better have a court order.
- For what? Who is this?
How many phones are you tapping? How
many agents are you doing surveillance on?
- Is this Agent Scully?
- Thank you.
You just answered all my questions.
(creaking)
Stop there! Right there!
Come on through the window nice and easy.
OK, I'm coming. It's me.
Your landlord.
I started fixing the antenna on the roof and...
I'm sorry, Mr Coeben. There was a man.
There was someone in the building.
Did you see anyone?
Yeah, you know him. Works with you.
Tall guy, brown hair.
Who? You don't mean Mulder?
Yeah, Mulder.
Mulder?
Are you in here?
(gasps)
(yells)
- (Frohike) It took serious voodoo.
- (Langly) Major satellite hacking.
- (Byers) But we got your data.
- (Skinner) What is it?
You're seeing real-time images
right off the JPL TOPEX/Poseidon.
We're wired right into the dish.
We can't find raw data
with UFO activity on it.
But Langly hacked into the data storage here
and pulled up something just as tasty.
This is UFO activity in the Pacific Northwest
just prior to Mulder's abduction.
These markers correspond with
reported alien abductions.
- It's a shopping spree.
- So Mulder's abduction...
Was a UFO whistle stop
on the way to the next pick-up.
Where? Where's the UFO activity
after Mulder's abduction?
We can't tell.
Not from the data we're pulling down.
If we can figure out where that ship
was going, where it's gonna be,
we've got a chance to find Mulder.
(knocks)
- Got a minute?
- Yeah, sure.
- You fly, Agent Doggett?
- Flying's for birds and baseballs. USMC, sir.
In Vietnam we used to fly night sorties
10ft above the treetops.
Before night vision, before fly-by-wire.
600 miles an hour and all we had
was an idiot gauge and our wits.
Guys used to say they only knew their
altitude by the smell of the VC rice pots.
You've come a long way, sir.
Usin' all the same instincts.
What can I do for you, Agent?
This task force, the search for Mulder...
- I'm runnin' it, right?
- You're the man in charge.
No one else is involved? Someone acting
under orders from another office?
I think I'd know, Agent.
What prompts the question?
My idiot gauge. My wits.
You got a chance to shine here, John,
stand in the spotlight.
Show them all you're an ace.
(door opens)
- What are you doing here?
- I could ask you the same.
- I came by to feed Mulder's fish.
- And then you got tired and took a nap.
You've got a way about you, Agent Doggett,
that might have worked with the NYPD,
but you're talking to a fellow FBI agent.
I'd appreciate some respect.
Respect like you showed me over the phone?
Give a little, get a little, Agent Scully.
Who ambushed me with the phoney chitchat
and then put a wiretap on my phone?
- That's BS.
- And now you're followin' me.
I just came by to feed the fish.
What do you want
to get on me, Agent Doggett?
What is it you hope to find?
- I'm just trying to find Mulder.
- You wouldn't know where to look.
It's in the desk, middle drawer.
- I know the answer, Agent Scully.
- I don't even know the question.
What happened to Mulder.
I know what you're gonna say, or not,
because you think I'm the big bad wolf.
Do you really believe it?
You think by talking in circles I'll just get
dizzy and blurt out this so-called answer?
- That he was abducted by aliens?
- You said it. I didn't.
I just find it hard to swallow that a scientist,
a serious person, could buy that.
Ever see an alien, Agent Scully?
You want me to go on record?
I will go on record to say this.
That I have seen things that I cannot explain.
I have observed phenomena
that I cannot deny.
And that, as a scientist
and a serious person,
it is a badge of honour not to dismiss these
things because someone thinks they're BS.
So you think he was abducted?
- I'm just trying to find him.
- Then what are you doing here?
Trying to figure these out.
I found them in his desk there.
Car rental receipts on Agent Mulder's Visa.
Four consecutive weekends in May.
Same mileage each trip.
370 miles, 375 miles.
Where was he going?
I don't know.
Like I said, maybe you really
didn't know your partner.
(cellphone rings)
John Doggett.
Agent Mulder at the FBI.
Assistant Director, follow me.
What's going on? What is this?
Mr Skinner, this way, please. You can
talk with Agent Scully after we're done.
Have a seat.
Someone came into this office after hours
and removed some material.
Files. We don't know exactly what just yet.
Who?
The office is secured by a pass-card lock and
whoever came in used Agent Mulder's card.
- You think Agent Mulder took the files?
- We're wondering about his state of mind.
In your statement you said,
prior to his disappearance,
Agent Mulder had felt threatened by the FBI.
No, that's not what I said. I said he felt the
X-Files were threatened by budget-cutting.
Is there anything you're not telling us
about Agent Mulder, or his attitude?
Do you think he'd ever
retaliate against the FBI?
- Agent Mulder was only after the truth.
- As are we, Assistant Director.
Agent Scully tells us she was home last night.
We see from your phone log you were here...
until at least after ten.
You think I came in here last night
using Agent Mulder's pass card?
You were the last person to see Mulder.
You and Agent Scully.
- Skinner is telling the truth.
- I believe him.
It still doesn't tell us
who used Mulder's card to get in.
- You think it was Mulder?
- I showed you those car rental receipts.
Now I find Agent Mulder's Visa was used
two days ago in Raleigh, North Carolina.
Two days ago?
By who? For what?
Flowers. Automatic debit to a mortuary there.
Mulder's mother is buried in Raleigh.
That's the reason
he was going every weekend.
It's one reason.
I don't know what to think.
I don't believe it, Dana.
It just doesn't make any sense to me.
All right. I got some light on this.
Maybe you can help me out here,
Agent Scully.
What is it?
Agent Mulder's medical records.
Recent stuff over the last year.
Did you know about a medical condition?
Either of you?
No.
A year ago, Agent Mulder
was hospitalised. Ring a bell?
- Something to do with his brain?
- His temporal lobe.
An undiagnosable condition, it says.
Irregular brain activity.
But he recovered. There was a full recovery.
Was there?
Mulder would have told us
if there was anything.
Would he?
He tell you about this?
About his headstone?
Mulder was dying.
What?
It's all right here.
For a year he was going to doctors.
There's a clear record of his decline.
How well did you really know him?
- How far would Mulder go?
- How far would he go for what?
The truth. His truth.
Whatever it was he was trying to prove.
How bad did he need to prove it?
- It was his whole life.
- What are you trying to say?
That Agent Mulder found himself
in a place none of us want to go.
Life threatened, work threatened,
and all for naught.
Nothing proven.
The effort in vain. No mark left.
Unless he rolled the dice,
took one big last chance to make it.
You think that Mulder was here,
that he broke in to steal those files.
Broke into your apartment, stole your
computer. Took his own computer.
Gathering it up.
To what?
To prove it?
Or cover it up. Create doubt.
I get Mulder, I get him.
I understand obsession, believe me.
But the question is, how far would he go?
So far as to stage his own disappearance?
I know what I saw.
I'm not gonna sit here and listen to this.
I watched it happen.
Agent Mulder?
Please don't report that.
I don't know what good it would do me.
It doesn't help me find Mulder.
That's not good enough.
These are records of microburst activity,
UFO activity since Mulder's abduction.
- I think this is a waste of time.
- Just look at them.
I see activity all over the southwestern states.
That's right.
Mulder disappeared in the Pacific Northwest.
And if Mulder is on that ship,
this is where he is now.
Here? In the Arizona desert?
This is what we have.
OK. Say this is true.
Then how do we even begin
to start finding him?
Maybe with whoever it is
they're looking to abduct next.
- We're only trying to help.
- We're only trying to find Mulder.
That's it.
- It just came to me.
- What?
What you saw. Why they took Mulder. Why
they're in Arizona now. It all makes sense.
(Scully) Why do people refuse
to believe in aliens and UFOs,
after all these years of sightings
and eyewitness accounts?
Why?
Because there's no real proof.
Because maybe, if there are aliens,
they're simply going around and removing
all the evidence before it becomes proof.
This isn't Mulder going around
and collecting this stuff, it's them.
(Skinner) Then why Arizona?
Because they are looking to find that which is
not in my computer, or Mulder's computer,
or in the files that were removed from the FBI.
They are looking to find
the whereabouts of good hard proof,
that in this case exists in a person.
In a boy named Gibson Praise.
This photograph's a few years old,
but take a look.
The objective in this case has been reframed.
The subject's name is Gibson Andrew Praise.
A child prodigy.
A pint-size chess champion, who Mulder
and Scully first investigated in
after a failed attempt on the boy's life.
His files were the ones we now believe
were stolen from this office.
In his investigation,
Agent Mulder came to believe
the boy was experiencing
abnormal brain activity.
Unexplained activity.
In his field notes here, he says
Gibson Praise could, and I quote:
"read people's thoughts".
Agent Mulder went so far in one report to
claim that the boy may have alien physiology.
Agent Mulder may be looking for the boy
who was last seen in Arizona.
So maybe to find Mulder
we first have to look for Gibson Praise.
Let's go, people. Let's move.
How do you want this handled?
I want you to put that on every TV station,
post office and fax machine in the Southwest.
I wanna make that face famous.
(yells)
Feel better?
I need some navigation.
To start looking for a 12-year-old kid
in the middle of the Arizona desert.
Well, there aren't a whole lot of choices.
I got a turn-off in five miles.
Do I take it or keep going straight?
Gibson Praise was last seen here, at a power
plant about 60 miles outside of Phoenix.
Though the satellite data shows activity here,
about a hundred miles to the north.
What's out there?
According to this map, a whole lot of nothin'.
This is Special Agent Crane
calling for Task Force Leader.
- John Doggett.
- Just confirmed a location on this kid.
He's at a school for the deaf
in a place called Flemingtown.
A dot on the map about 90 miles
from where I am now.
I talked to the school principal.
- Is the kid in school now?
- He lives there.
Have the principal put him someplace where
you can keep an eye on him until we arrive.
Gonna take me an hour or more get there.
I'm gonna see if I can cut some time off that.
There's a school 20 minutes from here.
Yes, sir. In his science class.
Is it important enough
to take him away from his studies?
I'll go and get him right now.
- Where's the boy?
- You have to explain a few things before...
- Is he down there?
- He's in my office.
Hi. We're looking for a boy
named Gibson Praise.
- Who are you?
- The kid went out the window.
- What are you doing here?
I'm trying to find Mulder.
The kid's on the move. Spread out!
The kid's on the loose!
You have the photo. Move!
(Gibson) Let me go.
Let me go.
(Doggett) Let the boy go!
Let him go, Mulder!
Visiontext Subtitles: Sarah Emery
(Child) I made this!