(music through headphones)
Hey, now we're talking.
Hey, right here, man! Right here!
Stop, you son of a...
You got highway hypnosis or something.
You didn't see me yellin' and wavin'?
You better watch that.
(air brakes hiss)
Come on. What now?
Where's everybody goin'?
Is the toilet broken? What?
Can someone please tell me
what's goin' on here?
No.
No!
(beep)
Damn.
(ringing tone)
- John Doggett.
- Hey. It's Scully. Good morning.
- Afternoon. I've been trying to reach you.
- Actually, I'm out of town.
I'm north of Sugarville, Utah, roughly.
Utah? What are you doing there?
The local coroner wants
a consultation on a murder victim.
A man who was found
beaten to death in the desert.
Apparently, his corpse shows
some anomalous characteristics.
- Anomalous? How?
- From what they're telling me,
he is a 22-year-old backpacker last seen by
his family six months ago in perfect health.
However, his body is now showing
advanced signs of osteoporosis,
arthritis and kyphosis of the vertebrae.
- He's got a spine of a 90-year-old woman.
- Sounds anomalous, all right.
- You didn't need me to tag along?
- It was just a simple consultation.
And he called me over the weekend,
and I figured I wasn't going to bother you.
- Well, if there's anything I can do from here.
- Actually, there might be, if you don't mind.
Somewhere in our files
there is an unsolved murder case.
Unfortunately, I don't remember any of the
particulars, like where or when it took place,
but I do remember that there were some
glycoproteins found at the crime scene.
- Glycoproteins.
- Yeah. Mucus.
But it was unable to be identified,
and, as you recently read through all of our
files, I thought it might ring a bell with you.
I don't have a great memory for mucus...
but I'll be happy to look.
Remember anything else?
Agent Scully?
- Agent Scully?
- I'm sorry?
- Do you remember anything else?
- No, no. Just... just mucus.
When you find that file, will you fax it over
to the Juab County Sheriff's office?
That's the best place to reach me.
My cellphone isn't working.
- All right. You got it.
- Thank you.
Hello?
(honks horn)
- How're you doin'?
- Good. Thanks.
I, uh... I was wondering...
A bus came through here a little while ago.
Do you happen to know
where it might have gone?
I was around back.
- Do you know what's up that road?
- Eventually Salt Lake, if you're not in a hurry.
Can I ask what happened to your hand?
I was... changing the blade on my bowsaw.
It's kind of gross.
Yeah.
There was a murder out here last week,
about 15, 20 miles off the state road.
Did you hear about it?
Yes, I did.
- It's scary.
- Yeah.
You should wash this out,
put iodine on it so it won't get infected.
- You sound like my mother.
- I also sound like a doctor.
- A medical doctor?
- Yeah.
Can you sell me some gas?
I'd love to, but I'm all out.
The tanker was supposed to be here
yesterday but... I'm hoping for this afternoon.
- How low are you?
- I got a quarter tank, I think. I'll make it.
- I'd feel awful bad if you didn't. Hang on.
- Thanks.
- Should be enough in here to tide you over.
- That's great. Thank you.
Do me a favour.
Don't go tellin' people that
I'm givin' away free gas back here.
Where is "here", exactly? Because
I can't seem to find this town on the map.
We're not really a town.
Just a few like-minded people
tryin' to keep the modern world at bay.
- You're good to go.
- Thank you very much.
Help is coming.
(engine splutters)
OK.
Hey! Excuse me.
You put something in my tank
that killed my engine.
What?
Where's that gas can?
I'd like to see it, please.
That's water. I barely even smell any gasoline.
Oh, God. You're right.
I'm sorry. I... I left it out.
It must have gotten rain in it.
It rains a lot here, does it?
As it's basically the desert.
- I'm really sorry.
- Yeah.
I'm going to use your phone.
I don't have one.
You don't have a phone.
So how did you call up the tanker
that was supposed to come here yesterday?
There's a phone up the street.
Mr Milsap's place. He'll help you out.
Hello?
- Hi.
- Mr Milsap?
- Can I help you?
Yes. I hope so. My car's stalled up the street.
I was wondering if I could use your phone.
Sure. It's in here.
- The line's dead.
- Oh, no.
Let me see.
Damn phone company.
They're updating the lines, so the service
gets interrupted. It'll come back on.
- How long?
- Ten minutes. Two hours.
I could say, but I'd just be guessing.
You're welcome to wait here.
I could even give you a room, if you like.
This was a boarding house.
I won't be here that long.
- What the hell is going on here?
- Sorry?
I get the distinct impression that
somebody doesn't want me to leave.
- I don't know anything about that.
- A bus came through here about an hour ago.
- Where did it go?
- A bus?
Don't tell me you didn't see it.
I think I'd have known
if a big bus came through.
Are you sure I can't
help you out with a room?
It's 18 miles to the state road.
Another 20 to Sugarville.
You don't want to walk it.
Excuse me!
Ma'am, excuse me.
Ma'am. Excuse me, ma'am.
Hello?
Ma'am, I need some help.
(sighs)
(knocking)
(Milsap) Doctor, can I speak to you?
It's... it's an emergency.
I'm sorry to bother you.
There's a man downstairs that needs help.
Please.
Let go. Don't hold him down.
- How long has he been seizing?
- Three... four minutes.
It's OK. You're all right. You're OK.
- What's his name?
- He's a stranger. He needed help.
- What's wrong with him?
- He had a grand mal seizure.
As far as I can tell, he's in status.
It's a continuous seizure state.
He doesn't smell like acetone, which
would indicate that he's hyperglycaemic.
He doesn't appear to have any head injuries.
He could be epileptic
and just ceased taking his medication.
How did this happen?
Uh-huh.
At any rate, we need to get him to a hospital.
Immediately.
I assume that your phone's still not working.
Sorry.
Do you or one of your friendly neighbours
happen to have a car?
- No one here has a car.
- No cars.
We could send someone
to the state road on foot.
All right? We could get them
to bring back help.
In the meantime, please,
anything you can do for him.
All right. Do you... Do you have
any Karo syrup? Any corn syrup?
Yeah.
(ringing tone)
Juab County Sheriff's office.
Sheriff Ciolino speaking.
Hi. This is Agent John Doggett with the FBI.
My partner, Agent Scully, requested
some material. What's your fax number?
Agent Doggett, when's your partner gonna
get here? The victim's family wants the body.
Agent Scully's not there?
- She was supposed to be there yesterday.
- That was our understanding.
Sheriff, could you send a car out?
Agent Scully is in Utah.
She called me yesterday
somewhere north of Sugarville.
- You got it. I'll get someone right out there.
- OK, thanks. I'll be in touch.
Danny, this is John Doggett.
I need you to trace a call for me.
It came to this office yesterday
about 1.30 in the afternoon.
Am I doing this right?
Yeah. You can hold off now.
- Nothing's happening.
- I'm sorry but...
I'm just winging it here.
Raising his blood sugar only helps if he has
hypoglycaemia. But it could be other things.
So what do we do?
I'm afraid that I have done all that I can do.
Unless you know how to get ahold of
diazepam or phenobarbital,
other than the nearest hospital -
which is where we should be, of course.
(coughs)
Hey.
Can you hear me?
How are you feeling?
- OK.
- Thank God.
Thank God.
We were all so scared.
- What can I do?
- I think I just need rest.
We should leave him alone.
Can you stay?
I'll go tell everybody.
- Are you a doctor?
- Yes, I am.
Thank you... for helping me.
I'm not sure if I've actually done anything.
In fact, I don't even know...
I don't even know
what's going on with you right now.
Do you know what your name is?
Um...
You don't remember, do you?
How about how you got here?
What about these people who have taken
you in? Do you know anything about them?
- They take good care of me.
- I'd say they take very good care of you.
The sun seems to rise and set on you.
In fact, they seem to have stranded me here
in order to nurse you back to health.
Why would they do that?
A murder took place about 20 miles
from here. A man was stoned to death.
His head was so badly crushed,
they couldn't identify him from his teeth.
It looks like upwards of a dozen people
may have participated
due to the footprints at the crime scene.
But it's a very tightknit group of people
who would murder together.
A cult, in a word.
And I'd say that these people qualify.
What are you? A detective?
FBI.
And I need to get you out of here,
but I don't know how.
Do you think that you can walk?
I don't know. I'm kind of weak.
I understand.
Hang on a second.
Let me just look at something, OK?
(Scully sighs)
(Squishing sound)
(groans)
That's starting to hurt.
Maybe you shouldn't do that.
Hold on.
(guttural grunting)
(ringing)
- Doggett.
- It's Ciolino.
The number you gave us is a payphone
a half-mile from the crime scene.
- Agent Scully must've just come from there.
- Looks like.
I'm sorry, still no sign of her.
- Are you canvassing neighbours?
- There's nobody to canvass.
It's a desolate area. There's nobody out there.
Help is coming from our Salt Lake City office.
I'm heading out there, too.
- There's a new angle to look at.
- What's that?
That payphone. Before Scully's call to me,
the last call on it was the night of the murder.
It was placed to a Juliette Gulatarski
of Fort Collins, Colorado.
She tells me it was her brother Hank.
He was on his way for a visit.
Said he was stuck in the desert
but would be there in two days.
He never showed.
Something's happening.
He's coming to.
Hey. Can you hear me?
How are you feeling?
I'm alive. That's a start.
- Oh, praise God.
- Praise him. Praise him!
What's wrong with me?
I just need some rest.
She can take care of me.
It's lucky they're still listening to you
for the time being.
This wound in your back?
It seems to be a point of entry
for a parasitic organism
that has taken up residence along your spine.
This is something
that I am completely unfamiliar with.
Oh, boy.
I don't know how far this extends
or how to get it out of you
without harming you.
- Does that mean I'm dying?
- You will die, if we cannot treat you properly.
These people don't seem
to want to let you go.
I think that they put this thing inside of you.
I have no idea
what the motives of these people are -
whether it's some bizarre
religious activity.
But they killed the last person
in your condition,
and I'm afraid that
they're going to try and kill you, too.
- This is a lot to take in.
- No kidding.
- What are you gonna do?
- I'm gonna try and get us the hell out of here.
These people tell me that they have no cars.
I don't believe 'em.
They've got to have transportation
hidden around here somewhere.
- I'm gonna take a look around, OK?
- You're not gonna be gone long, right?
- You know how to use a gun?
- Pretty much.
- I'll be back soon.
- The sooner the better.
(knocking)
Where did she go?
She says I'm dying.
We need another swap.
- Sheriff? Agent John Doggett.
- You made good time.
Agent Brian Mayfield, Salt Lake office.
- We're at your disposal.
- Appreciate it.
Sheriff, does this wound look familiar?
- It's the victim in our morgue.
- That's not your murder victim.
That's a photo of a John Doe
found off a West Texas highway in .
- Our guy has the same wound.
- Yeah, I thought you were gonna say that.
Arizona, '93.
New Mexico, '97.
Nevada, '99.
All four had their brains beaten out and were
dumped in remote areas. All unsolved cases.
- How'd you run these down?
- Agent Scully had me trace this first one.
It noted glycoproteins at the crime scene,
which is what she found.
This same wound kept showin' up.
These murders ranged throughout
the Southwest, zigzagging all over the desert.
The more remote the better.
Hey. How'd you...
You had me convinced.
(Scully grunts angrily)
I'm a federal agent! At this moment,
the FBI is searching for me!
They won't find you.
(Hank) Doctor.
Your life... is about to take a wonderful turn.
You're going to become a part of something
much, much greater than you are.
You're going to be... so loved.
Amen. Amen!
(QTOUD) Amen.
No!
You son of a bitch!
- Amen!
- You just murdered him!
- (group) Amen!
- Amen!
No.
No!
I'm pregnant!
No! No, don't do this!
I'm gonna have a baby!
No! Don't do this!
No!
I'm gonna have a baby!
No! No!
No!
(Scully crying out with pain)
What did you put in me?!
I'm gonna get
every last one of you bastards!
No.
(SCUM groans)
You'll love us. You'll protect us.
You'll teach us,
make us better than we are.
We're taught not to envy,
but I do envy you so.
That you'll soon be one with him.
Him?!
That thing in my spine is a "him"?!
(cries out with pain)
Please.
This is such a wonderful, wonderful thing
for you...
and your unborn child.
That last man just wasn't
a suitable tabernacle.
The thing of it is,
there's always the chance
that your body won't fail him,
that he'll be in you for ever.
(vehicle approaching)
Help!
(muffled) Help!
- Good evening.
- You lost?
- Maybe. I'm way off the main road, for sure.
- Can we help you?
- I hope so. I'm...
looking for this woman.
Have you seen her?
No. Can't say I have.
Help!
She would have been driving
a rental car like mine.
- You sure she hasn't been through here?
- No.
We get so few visitors,
we remember each one pretty well.
All right. Thanks for your time.
Help!
(vehicle leaves)
(grunts)
- Sheriff, this is Doggett.
- I read you, Agent Doggett. Where are you?
20 miles off the state road, just north
of the crime scene. Some kind of outpost.
I'm gettin' a definite vibe from it.
I talked to a guy who had a gun in his pocket-
and I don't mean he was happy to see me.
I'll send everybody I've got.
Hurry. I can't wait for you.
(moaning)
(loud groaning)
Hey.
(grunting)
God Almighty. Agent Scully.
- Agent Scully.
- (muffled moans)
(gasps for breath) Agent Doggett.
Get me the hell out of here.
- Can you walk?
- I don't know.
- How far is your car?
- It's about a half-mile up the road.
I know something closer.
(Scully cries out)
- Can you hot-wire it?
- Can I hot-wire it?!
Gone in 60 seconds, Jack.
We're gonna strand these lunatics.
- (groans)
- Agent Scully.
- Talk to me.
- You gotta cut it out.
Cut it out. (groans)
Now it's gonna come to my brain.
Cut it out of me now!
(Scully screams with pain)
(Scully pants)
(Scully screams)
Just do it, Doggett!
(pounding on walls)
Why?
(approaching sirens)
- Ready to go?
- Yeah, I'm ready to go.
Grand jury convenes today.
All 47 cult members are sticking together.
Their defence is that they're being persecuted
for their religious beliefs.
They believe they worshipped Christ.
That that thing was the Second Coming.
Look, I... I wanted to apologise.
I left you out of this case,
and that was a mistake on my part.
It was almost a fatal mistake.
It was. You screwed up.
- And I won't do it again.
- I appreciate it.
Visiontext Subtitles: Doreen Trenerry
(Child) I made this!