Pick up! Pick up the phone!
Look, I don't know what that bitch told you,
but I'm solid. She's lying to you.
Check her right-hand desk drawer.
It's all there - the whole story.
Pick up, man!
Call him off and let's talk about this,
all right? Give me a chance to explain.
- Help me! Somebody wants to kill me!
- Who wants to kill you?
- He's out there!
- Hold up!
Hold on. Don't do that, guy!
You calm down...
- We've got to stop him!
- Who?
He's out there!
We have to get him before he gets me!
- Hey, hey! Hey! Get off!
- Take him down, take him down!
No! Let me up!
He's gonna kill me!
Take it easy. Relax now. Settle down.
No.
This isn't enough! I'm not safe in here!
Hey, buddy, you've never been safer
in your life, OK? Just relax.
He can get me in here!
- I'll go call Social Services.
- Right.
It's not enough!
He can get to me! He...
They've identified it
as nine-millimetre pistol ammunition.
Teflon coated, armour piercing.
It's a single round.
He was shot. No doubt about that.
So I assume
the million-dollar question is how?
Yeah. What do we know about the victim?
Carlton Chase, age 39. Well-to-do realtor,
single, lived in the area all his life.
Nothing but parking tickets on his record.
Came tearing in last night
saying someone was gonna kill him.
- He was right.
- Except I don't see bullet holes in the walls.
The round looks to have entered
through the top of his head.
Agents.
Thanks for coming down so quick.
- Al Triguero.
- John Doggett. Agent Scully.
I'd appreciate any help you can give us.
We got this much figured out so far.
- Bullet came through the air vent.
- Yeah, that's how it's looking.
There's a burr on this louvre here
where the bullet passed through.
You can barely see it, but it's there.
So I'm thinking
this is where the killer hid.
He somehow got into this ventilation system,
and from here he had
a clear line of sight to shoot Chase below.
Did anyone hear a gunshot?
Seems likely you'd hear one. Even with
a silencer, it'd echo through the ductwork.
What's directly above this?
I don't understand. How could
someone make that shot from here?
They didn't make it from here.
- Can I use your pencil?
- Sure.
Captain, we're gonna need
your crime scene investigators up here.
You got it.
- So, lucky shot?
- Very.
But this victim stated that he was gonna
be killed just moments before he was shot,
which doesn't sound lucky at all.
I guess I can't argue with that.
- What you got there?
- The old Godfather trick.
Wrap a towel around a pistol
to muffle the sound.
The killer was up here all right.
So how in the hell did he make that shot?
There's thermal-imaging technology
which can pick up body heat through walls.
- Maybe that's what allowed him to aim.
- We field-tested that in the Marines.
It weighs close to 90 pounds,
has to be cooled with liquid nitrogen.
I can't quite see somebody
lugging it up that ladder we just climbed.
Either way, the rooftop of a police station?
That's a pretty ballsy place for a hit.
(Dew)
(Chase) Pick up! Pick up the phone!
Look, I don't know what that bitch told you,
but I'm solid. She's lying to you.
Check her right-hand desk drawer.
It's all there - the whole story. Pick up...
What are you doing?
My... printer cable is loose.
And that's more important than coffee?
- Any messages?
- No.
The light's blinking.
Looks like a message to me.
Are you gonna play it or what?
Stupid ain't cute, Tammi.
I don't care what your mama says.
(Dew)
(man) Yeah... I got, like, rats again.
I need you to get them all this time.
1806 Brook Valley Turnpike.
Last name Allesandry.
You've been here before.
- Dwight?
- Yeah, I got it.
No. Did you hear the news
this morning? Carlton Chase?
I just thought it was pretty scary news.
Try and get Randall on the phone.
(footsteps)
Randall?
Your brother wants to see you.
You avoiding me?
Tammi told you
I wanted to talk to you, right?
You wanna tell me
what happened last night?
Randall, I'm not mad at you necessarily,
but I need to know exactly what happened.
Anytime you do something without telling
me first, you could get us both into trouble.
I saw him stealing.
- Carlton stealing from me?
- Yeah.
He was skimming.
So, where's the money
that he was skimming?
You see, the thing of it is, Randall,
you get the money, then you do your thing.
It's a simple equation.
That's what I'm talking about
when I say you need to talk to me first!
We'll probably be OK.
But in the future...
let's keep the communication lines open.
One hand talks to the other, right?
Here, I brought you a sandwich.
Meat loaf the way you like it.
Go ahead, take it.
It's got mayonnaise and ketchup.
We going out tonight?
Police station's less than a mile from here.
Chase ran it on foot.
He says that somebody was after him.
This is probably where it all started.
- Huh.
- What's that?
Chase did business with an exterminating
company called AAA-1 Surekill.
Six jobs in one month.
I know that's a requirement
of selling a house.
Agent.
It's a .45.
The bullet that killed Chase
at the police station was a nine millimetre.
You know, Elvis used to do this
to his hotel rooms.
I think Carlton Chase did this.
So who was he shooting at?
If it was someone in this room,
he sure would've hit 'em.
Unless it was someone outside.
- You got the cash?
- What's this look like?
- Who the...
- Evening.
- What? You lost?
- Nope. I think this must be the place.
- What, you a cop?
- Oh, hell, no.
No, your secret's safe with me, fellas.
But I will be taking that money
off your hands and the dope.
Oh, you're funny.
Nah, you know what? Chris Rock is funny.
And you? You're just dead.
Cap his ass.
Bang.
(Doggett) Yeah, I got it.
Nine millimetre. Sulphuric.
No, I got it.
All right. Thanks.
So which kind of shooting was this:
lucky, coincidental or some third alternative?
It's precision marksmanship, that's for sure.
These holes line up perfectly
with the three victims behind there,
which tells me that the shooter
was standing right here behind this wall.
And consequently wouldn't be able
to see what the hell he's aiming at.
Unless he could see.
The light our eyes can register is only
one portion of the electromagnetic spectrum.
Other wavelengths, from infrared
to gamma, have other properties.
X-rays, for instance,
can pass through solid objects.
Walls, for example.
So, you're saying this guy
used some kind of x-ray machine.
You're not saying this guy has x-ray vision?
I'm remarking that these wavelengths exist.
And the only thing that is stopping us
from seeing them, if you will,
is the biochemical structure of our eyes.
I'm conjecturing that
if this structure were somehow different,
we'd have the ability
to see things that we don't.
Call in Clark Kent.
OK, so you explain it.
- I can't, so I'm sticking with what I do know.
- Which is?
That this was a drug rip-off.
Furthermore, it's the fifth drug rip-off
in this area in the past two months.
Somebody's making a living
capping drug dealers.
And how does a dead
real-estate agent figure into that?
Well, that I don't know... yet.
But I did find out one more thing.
Sulphuryl fluoride.
You got a moment to see me in my office?
Dwight, I need to get this to the bank.
It can wait.
Can't you tell your brother
to get some lunch or something at least?
He's practically right outside the door.
I'll keep the noise level down, if you will.
- I just feel like he's always watching me.
- How's he watching you now?
Hello?
- Anybody here?
- Yeah.
Agents Doggett and Scully, FBI.
Dwight Cooper.
- What can I do for you?
- Mr Cooper, do you recognise these?
I don't recognise much of anything
except shapes. Tammi!
Tammi, come look at this for me.
I got bad peepers. Legally blind since birth.
This look familiar?
They're ours. They're last
month's billings for Mr Chase.
Oh. Carlton.
One of my best clients.
I sent him a ham every Christmas
till he finally told me he was a Jew.
He was a nice guy.
We found some evidence at a crime scene.
A piece of fabric on which we found
traces of a chemical. Sulphuryl fluoride.
It's an insecticide used only
by licensed exterminators.
Yeah, it's good stuff. We use it, along
with about 200 other outfits in central Mass.
You've done time, haven't you?
Yeah, a long time ago.
Now my brother and I are actually members
of the Worcester Chamber of Commerce.
- Anything else?
- Yeah.
Why did Carlton Chase call this office
14 minutes before he was murdered?
8.34pm. We found a call to your office
billed on Mr Chase's calling card.
It was made from a payphone
not far from where he was murdered.
Wow.
I don't know what to tell you.
We were all gone home by that time, and
there wasn't any message on our machine.
All right. We'll be in touch
if we have any further questions.
Tammi.
What do you know about that?
About Carlton calling here?
He...
I guess he must have left a message.
What did it say?
I didn't hear it.
I was reaching for the play button,
and I hit the erase button by mistake.
I should have told you. I was just afraid
that I lost us some business maybe.
Come here, baby.
You know I can't see worth a damn.
I just want to have a look at your eyes.
The eyes are the windows of the soul.
They tell you everything you need
to know about a person.
So tell me.
Are you filing?
No, Dwight.
That's all I needed to know.
- Dwight Cooper, arrested in 1986.
- For grand theft auto.
Right. How does
a legally blind guy steal a car?
I assume that he had a partner
who did the driving.
That brother he mentioned - Randall Cooper.
They were arrested together. Although
Randall apparently didn't serve much time.
They share the same birthday.
- They're twins.
- I hate twins.
Twins never rat each other out.
Maybe there's someone
in that office who will.
Hey, Tammi. You're here early.
You know you accidentally
left your car running?
You must have been in a real hurry
to get in here and make the coffee.
What you got there?
Can I see?
(Doggett) Dwight Cooper, FBI.
Dwight Cooper, warrant to search.
Have someone read it to you.
What the hell are you looking for?
Evidence related to the murder
of Carlton Chase, et al.
What's in the box?
You got me.
What's the combination?
I don't remember.
So much for the easy way.
You owe me for that.
I run a clean business.
Nothing here will say otherwise.
I wouldn't be so sure.
Can you explain these, Mr Cooper?
Mr Cooper, you want to tell me
about these invoices?
OK, Randall.
Let's talk about your
exterminating company.
It's just the three of you, right?
You and your brother and Tammi Peyton?
So how is it that your little company
billed over $700,000
to Chase Realty last year?
$700,000.
That's a lot of dead rats.
I think that you and your brother
and Carlton Chase
were in a whole other business together.
Man, I gotta get into the bug business.
I had no idea you could make so much dough
killing things that creep around behind walls.
You are quite the entrepreneur.
I'm just a regular Joe,
providing a public service.
Randall?
I'm just a regular Joe.
Provide a public service.
Is that what your brother
just said to Agent Doggett?
You know why I said that, don't you?
Because somehow...
you can see through that wall.
You can see your brother behind me
and you can read his lips.
I don't know what gives you the ability,
but I know how you use it.
You shoot drug dealers
from places where they can't see you,
and then you and Dwight rob them.
That's how you make all that money, isn't it?
No. We're exterminators.
Yeah.
You certainly are.
And talking to you now,
I think that the whole thing is Dwight's idea.
It's time to be your own man, Randall.
It's time to think for yourself.
You tell them anything?
No, I said what you said.
We got a problem.
It needs to be taken care of.
I just keep the books.
You keep the books on a lot of blood money
going through that office.
We're supposed to believe you didn't know?
The drug rip-offs, the murders?
I didn't know about any of that.
Dwight doesn't tell me anything.
I just book the cash receipts.
I don't ask where they're from.
I know not to ask.
Look, here's where I get confused,
and I'm hoping that you can help me out.
Carlton Chase.
We think Chase was Dwight's fence.
He sold the drugs your boss stole.
Together, they had a good thing going.
So why was Chase killed?
It seems like bad business.
Unless the reason wasn't business.
Unless it was personal.
Am I under arrest?
Tammi Peyton's phone records.
Found something interesting.
Calls to Carlton Chase.
All of 'em late night.
What do you want to bet
they weren't discussing escrow accounts?
So Dwight Cooper learns something's going
on between his girlfriend and Carlton Chase.
And he kills him. Or he orders him killed,
assuming Randall's the triggerman.
- (Scully) Maybe not.
- (Doggett) What do you mean?
(Scully) Maybe Dwight's
not the one who's jealous.
I know it was you.
I still need help, Randall.
I made a reservation for
the three-o'clock bus. You go wait for me.
It's right over there - the Big Sky Express.
I'll be back right after I get the money.
I know you took that book
to protect me from Dwight.
I need my book, Randall.
I can't get my money without it.
I'll be back in half an hour, OK?
I'll meet you by the bus.
Randall. You know I'm coming back.
You saved me from Carlton. I owe you.
Randall.
I'll meet you by the bus.
Clothes are gone.
Tammi left in a hurry.
- Maybe she thought someone was after her.
- If someone's after you, you don't pack.
- You think she planned to go?
- I do. The question is where?
- Who you calling?
- Whoever Tammi called last.
(male voice) Welcome to Concordia
Bus Lines. Our menu options have changed.
For reservations, press one.
- Tammi.
- (gasps) Dwight!
Is this what you had
in your little secret box? Hm?
A safety-deposit key. Looks like you
had a lot of my money in there.
- Dwight.
- Shut up and drive.
Drive!
So this is how you did it, hmm?
You kept two sets of books.
Huh. You've been
ripping me off for months.
There's $100,000 difference here. Explains
why you were in a hurry the other morning.
- Dwight.
- Shut up!
Randall should've killed you, not Chase.
Or maybe you and Carlton
were working together?
It wasn't like that.
When Carlton found out about the money,
he blackmailed me. He made me... do things.
Aw, I bet you put up a big fight.
No, wait a minute. If Carlton wasn't stealing
from me, then why did Randall kill him?
Dwight, you don't understand.
No, no, no. I do understand.
My brother was sweet on you.
He killed Carlton because he knew
what was going on between the two of you.
Where the hell you been? Hm?
I got something for you to do.
(Dwight) Randall, get over here!
Dwight, no.
Take it!
She ripped us off, Randall, and you knew it.
No, Randall.
Did you think the two of you were gonna
run off into the sunset together?
She used you.
Look at me, Randall.
I'm the one who loves you. Not her.
Not anybody else.
Cos we're blood.
That's thicker than anything.
I'm gonna walk away now.
And I'm gonna think hard
about how I can forgive you.
You know what you gotta do.
Randall?
You're not gonna do this.
Randall, please.
I was coming back for you.
No, you weren't.
Randall!
No!
Agent. Has he said anything?
A county DA came in
and he declined representation.
Aside from that,
he's been uncommunicative.
APB on Tammi Peyton's a wash so far.
The Bureau in Montana's on alert.
He watched her every day,
wherever she was.
A man who can look at anything
in the world, and he chooses her.
He must have seen something in her
she couldn't see in herself.
If you're suggesting
he could see into her heart, Agent...
I think we're out of FBI territory on this one.
I'll be out front.
Visiontext Subtitles: Yasmin Rammohan
(Child) I made this!