(Scully) We live in a darkness
of our own making,
blind to a habitant world all but unseen by us.
A world of beings
travelling through time and space
imaginable to us only as flights of fancy.
Who are these beings we dare to imagine,
but fear to accept?
What dark work goes on
inside their impossible machines,
cloaked from us by invisible forces?
If they know our secrets,
why can't we know theirs?
(boy) Stop it, please. No!
Stop it. Let me go.
- Let me go.
- (man) Let the boy go!
Let him go, Mulder!
Let him go, or I will be
compelled to use my weapon.
I don't want to do that.
I don't want to shoot.
Now, are you armed?
Come on, damn it. This is just stupid.
Don't turn this into a movie.
Just tell me if you've got a gun.
It's too hot for this BS!
All right, then, lie down.
Lie down on the ground.
Keep your hands out.
Lay down on your belly there.
For crying out loud, what are you doing?
Agent Mulder, stay there!
He went over! Over the edge!
Who?
Mulder.
All right. I'll talk to Scully.
You guys head back to the school.
Where is he? Where's Mulder?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
An agent said on the radio you saw him.
I saw him back right off that cliff
and I saw him fall right over there.
- (Skinner) Then where is he?
- Gone.
- Come on. He can't be gone.
- He can't be, but he is.
That cliff there? He fell from there?
It's impossible, a fall like that.
A cop sees things. A man drops five stories,
dusts his head off and goes back to work.
An old lady gets shot in a restaurant,
plucks the slug out of her egg foo yung.
But even if Mulder survives this,
what he does then is too much.
You got your point of impact there,
clear and identifiable.
And a set of tracks here
leading down to the wash.
Look at these tracks. What do you see?
Mulder was running.
- It wasn't Mulder.
- That's the one thing I'm sure of.
It may have looked like Mulder,
but it wasn't Mulder.
I told you I knew Mulder.
OK, maybe I didn't know him that well.
But I know who was up there,
and it was Fox Mulder.
I'm sure it did look like Mulder and
you have every reason to believe it was him.
But it was not Mulder.
I told you that I've seen things,
things that I can't explain.
Well, I have seen what looks like a man
transform into another man.
What looks like a man,
but who's not a man?
- So what is he?
- You don't wanna know.
If he's not a man, what the hell is he?
Don't turn your back on me.
I'm asking you a legitimate question.
He's alien.
- He's a bounty hunter.
- Looking to collect a bounty on...?
On Gibson Praise...
because he's part alien.
He's a human anomaly.
This alien bounty hunter disguised himself
as Mulder to come out here and grab the boy?
To take him back to his ship,
where we believe Mulder is.
You know, Agent Scully, you're starting
to remind me a lot of Agent Mulder yourself.
Well, then, you explain it to me.
If it's true or possible that there's someone
like this out there, this bounty hunter,
he could just become anyone.
You, me, any damn one of us.
I think that it is true.
And possible.
And wherever Mulder is right now...
he better damn well be smiling.
(woman) Is this authorised?
(vehicle approaching)
Right. They're here.
- Any sign of him, of Mulder?
- Not according to these people.
We went through the school.
- You're better than this.
- Sir?
He's gotta be here somewhere.
Let's search the school again.
(cracking)
(footsteps approaching)
Hello?
Sorry. I thought you were...
I thought they'd cleared you out of here.
Find something?
No. Let's keep looking.
- Administration building is clear.
- Copy. Check it again.
I want to know how Doggett got here.
How did he even know where we were going?
I don't know, but he'll turn this place
upside down looking for the wrong person.
- What happened to Gibson Praise?
- Whatever happened to him, he's long gone.
Wherever he is,
he's three steps ahead of us.
We've got a pair of eyeballs on us.
Start walking. I'll be behind you.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
You shouldn't have come here.
You shouldn't have come.
You'll lead them to me.
I'm here to protect you, Gibson.
I know you know that's the truth.
I know you know my thoughts.
I know they took the man
you work with - Mulder.
And now they've come to take me.
The only reason they wanna take you, Gibson,
is because you're a special boy.
They wanna take you
because of what you are.
I'm sorry. I didn't know that
someone was following me.
My friend Thea knows.
She's the only one at school I've told.
She says the FBI is looking for me, too.
She's afraid for me.
She has a right to be afraid.
We don't know who to trust now.
- I fell when I was running away.
- You might have broken it.
If they find me, they'll take me.
I know it. I've always known it.
I'm gonna make you a splint, Gibson, OK?
I can set your leg, but I'm gonna
need a car to get you out of here.
I'm gonna come back for you. I promise.
I'm not gonna let anything bad
happen to you.
You said that to me once before.
(cellphone rings)
Yeah? Deputy director for you.
- This is John Doggett.
- I'm getting reports from Arizona...
- Yes, sir.
- ..that you found Agent Mulder.
Somebodyjumped the gun on that.
I saw him, but I...
What do you mean you saw him?
What the hell is going on out there?
I've got local SAR, a rolling ground cordon
and an eye in the sky. We're on top of it.
How does the FBI find a man
and then lose him
in the middle of the desert?
Cos I'd like to know.
- Are you there?
- Yeah, I heard the question.
I put you in charge out there.
Now do the damn job!
This amuse you? I amuse you?
No. ltjust made sense to me.
How you found your way here,
who led you to Gibson.
- You think I was spying on you?
- No, but I think our new deputy director was.
You're being made a pawn
in a rigged game.
You painted me the picture.
Now put it in a frame.
All right.
You got a good rep, Agent Doggett.
You don't compromise, you don't quit.
You're a damned good FBI agent.
Lot of guys put you
in the director's chair one day.
Which is why you've been set up to fail.
No amount of rolling cordons
or eyes in the sky will turn up Mulder.
It's just the wrong approach.
It's not a question of approach.
It's the only approach I got.
The only way you're gonna find Mulder
is to give in to the truth.
To listen to Scully.
But even then, say you do find him,
even then you lose.
You put anything about aliens or UFOs
or alien bounty hunters in your report,
Kersh will ruin you.
I'm betting that was his plan.
Is Agent Scully here?
Where's Agent Scully?
I need someone who's with Agent Scully
to put her on a radio.
Someone with Agent Scully.
Anyone got a 20 on Agent Scully?
Is anyone out there with her?
- I'm with Agent Scully.
- Then who's this?
Go for Agent Scully.
What?
Give me the radio.
- You're with Scully?
- Across the room from her.
From who? From me?
Where?
- What room? Where are you?
- Bunkhouse.
We're in the dorm.
Tell him to hold her.
Tell him not to let her out of his sight!
Hold Scully. We're coming to you.
Agent Scully!
(choking)
Hey!
There she is!
Do you see her?
- Where did she go? Did you see her?
- No.
She ran right back here!
I saw her!
You saw her!
(gasping)
Agent, can you breathe?
He thinks it was me.
He thinks that I did this to him.
How is that possible?
It's someone in this room.
Mulder!
(Siren)
Agent Scully?
Where are you going?
Agent Scully!
Get out of the car.
- Who are you?
- Who am I?
- Drop it and turn around!
- No.
Just do it! I know how it works.
Kill shot to the back of the neck.
You're pointing your weapon at a friend.
Turn around, or I'll assume that
you're not who you say you are.
Scully, it's me! Skinner!
I can prove it.
I know your secret. Who else knows it?
OK. Then tell me.
You tell me. How do I know it's you?
I don't like pointing guns
at pregnant women
any more than I like them
pointing guns at me.
This has gone too far, Scully.
No. That's what's wrong here.
It hasn't gone far enough.
- I need those car keys.
- And what are you gonna do?
Look, we are being hampered here
by the FBI,
by John Doggett,
by doubt, by our own mistrust.
Whatever it is, it is working
as long as we let it.
You told me Mulder wouldn't allow it.
Wouldn't let me ruin my career over this.
Over him.
But what about you, Scully? I mean,
my God, you've got even more at stake.
I can't take the chance
that I'm never gonna see him again.
Mulder could just come walking
out of the dark. We don't know.
Look, we've got one last chance here
waiting for us out there in the desert.
Gibson Praise.
It may just be who gets to him first.
Get in the car. I'll drive.
Gibson!
He's not down there.
I told him to stay here.
He was supposed to stay here.
Gibson!
I found him.
Gibson?
What are you doing out here?
Why didn't you answer me, huh?
He's here.
I hear him.
What are you talking about?
Mulder.
He's somewhere out there.
He's got a really bad fever.
I think his leg might be infected.
We gotta get you to the hospital.
OK, buddy?
You're so close now.
OK.
Put your arm around my neck.
Watch your leg.
- Agent Scully.
- You take him to the hospital.
What about you?
I got a boy here who needs
emergency medical attention!
What?
Are you OK? What's wrong?
It's OK, Gibson. Lie down. Lie down.
Mulder!
Oh, my God.
(helicopter engine)
For someone who claims he's not
following me, you sure have a knack.
- You're where the action is.
- Does that tell you I'm crazy or I'm right?
Wandering around in the desert
in the dead of night, you call it.
You say you want to find Mulder,
but you won't do what it takes.
- You're afraid I'm right.
- I'm not afraid of anything.
Except that Mulder's got even you
believing in this crap.
You've seen this "crap" for yourself now.
How do you explain what took place today?
Let me ask you something hypothetically.
If you were to find him out here,
or this ship, or this alien bounty hunter,
- what would you do then?
- I know what Agent Mulder would do.
- He'd do whatever it took.
- You mean lie. Like you've been lying to me.
And flout orders like you've done
every step of the way. Is that what it takes?
Give a little, get a little!
You knew where the kid was
and wouldn't tell me. Why?
What kid? I don't see any kid.
You're lying to me again! Assistant Director
Skinner took him from here to the hospital.
How do you know that?
There's one thing I know
for sure in this case,
and that's that Mulder is after this boy
Gibson Praise. Why? It beats me.
But when he goes after that kid,
my men will be waiting for him.
Your men followed
Assistant Director Skinner?
Where you going?
Agent Scully, where are you going?
Your men are at the hospital?
I got it controlled.
Nobody goes in or out of that building.
How do you know that they're your men?
Scully!
- Where's the boy?
- Door at the end of the hall, with AD Skinner.
Are you certain?
My agents have a visual on the window. The
nurse has checked the boy every 20 minutes.
Personnel is going about their business.
We're just waiting for Mulder.
Every minute that you wait,
that boy's in danger. He's exposed.
No one's getting past us, Agent Scully.
No one's gotten past us.
You believe that, Agent Doggett?
If something tries to rip your throat out,
I got you covered.
AD Skinner.
This is John Doggett!
What the hell is this?
What the hell's going on?
There's no one in that room.
I'm looking for a patient, a boy, 12 years old.
He may still be in this building.
The window doesn't open.
How's a man and a boy get out of here,
except by that door?
(creaking)
Agent Scully.
It's OK. I've got him. Gibson.
How did you get here?
- How did you get him out of that room?
- We went up through the ceiling.
I don't know who to trust.
Where is he?
He's right here.
They're gonna find him.
(yells)
(gunshot)
Agent Scully!
An agent needs help!
I said an agent needs help!
The best I can say is
it's lucky it all happened in a hospital.
Very lucky, yes, sir.
I assume the hazardous materials
which caused this must have been medical.
That has not yet been determined.
So much here is undetermined.
As remain the whereabouts of Mulder.
But some of your "facts"...
like "a man falls from a cliff
and disappears",
"an agent has his throat crushed
by an assailant who vanishes into thin air."
This reads like potboiled science fiction.
You mean it reads like an X-File.
But that's what you intended, wasn't it,
when you assigned me to the case?
I'll ask the questions, John.
You just give me some damn answers.
Don't come back until you do.
My dad always said
it's not who wins or loses,
it's who takes the worst beating that counts.
- Is that supposed to cheer me up?
- I thought so.
But then I never did get to see your opponent.
And you never will.
You still don't believe me.
What I don't believe is
how long they're keeping you here.
It's just some things
they have to check out... make sure of.
I've got some things
I thought you'd want checked out.
AD Skinner is in stable condition,
resting comfortably and
awaiting diagnosis and further study.
Ditto Agent Landau's throat.
Gibson Praise is now a ward of the state,
but I asked for special protection,
as I assumed you would yourself.
- What are you doing here, Agent?
- Keeping you apprised of the case.
That's not your job.
It is, actually.
And officially.
I'm... assigned now to the X-Files.
Whatever you and I may differ on,
I'll find him, Agent Scully.
Visiontext Subtitles: Tram Nguyen Zelniker
(Child) I made this!