A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
Work together to make it move...
and make the pedestal table vibrate.
- It's vibrating like crazy.
- That's impressive.
We're gonna fucking prank them.
This is a blue stone.
It's a ghost.
Three comedians.
Hi, ghost lovers.
- Hi, Insta-story.
- We're about to go in the castle.
A haunted place.
- Poulpe! Bérengère!
- Thomas?
Paranormal missions.
I don't feel well.
Traps.
Challenges.
- Are you ready to try the mission?
- Totally.
For the most scared...
a punishment.
Hello. This is Thomas.
A game that's going to last...
until dawn.
SOMEWHERE IN DORDOGNE...
Do you believe in ghosts or not?
I do, yeah.
I believe in energies, entities...
- ...in souls.
- He's already laughing.
- You don't?
- I was laughing at the word "entities."
If that exists, everything
we've seen in horror movies is real.
I believe when we die,
- we leave our physical sheath...
- Body, yeah.
...and we become energy,
like electricity or something.
So, it's scary because we can't see it.
If ghosts can go wherever they want,
why don't they go to Tahiti?
The soul is done--
Why don't ghosts go to Tahiti?
- I would definitely go.
- Yeah, take it easy.
Well, I don't know about Tahiti,
but, in any case, there are ghosts here...
in the Château de Puymartin,
which will be their playground...
tonight.
Our three friends
are only a few kilometers
from this 13th-century building,
which was the epic scene
of a terrible domestic tragedy.
"A dark legend,
a violent and jealous spouse...
a young woman
held prisoner for 15 years...
a lover hanged from a tree...
a walled-in corpse,
and ghosts..."
Badass.
No, not badass,
because the goal of tonight's game
is to face your fears...
- Fuck.
- There are so many!
Haunted mosquitoes.
...and finally get out of the car
to play with the others' fears.
Go, Bérengère. We're right behind you.
Fuck.
Bérengère seems on high alert,
but the other two are a little relaxed.
I don't think they understand
the house is haunted...
and that at dawn, a punishment
awaits the biggest chicken.
It's mega happy in here.
Happily scary!
Puymartin consists of tours, a dungeon,
a big living room, a small living room,
and squeaky doors.
Go on in. Someone needs to oil this.
Headquarters.
Walkie-talkies, monitoring screens
connected to surveillance cameras,
a pool table, and weird knick-knacks.
A Berrier.
Are you okay, Thomas?
Yeah, I-- No.
Yeah, it's a Berrier.
They have all the real ghost hunter gear.
Let the game begin!
MIDNIGHT - SIX HOURS BEFORE DAWN
"Mission number one.
In the 16th century, after returning
from battle, Jean de Saint-Clar
caught his wife, Thérèse,
in the arms of her lover.
Thérèse was imprisoned,
and the lover was executed,
then hanged from a tree
where Thérèse could see.
Imprisoned for 15 years
in the north tower..."
I want to say,
"Thank you, Jean Saint-Clar."
"When she died, her corpse was walled in
so she could never find peace,
even in the afterlife."
"Goal of the mission:
try to contact Jean de Saint-Clar
to find out if he regrets his actions."
- That's the pissed off husband.
- Yeah.
Have to contact the guy
who walled in his woman for 15 years.
MISSION ONE
THE HUSBAND
First mission:
contact the spirit
of Thérèse's bad-tempered husband.
Bad-tempered enough
to hang a guy from a tree
and lock up his wife for 15 years.
Yeah, pretty bad-tempered.
Even so, the guys
don't seem very bothered by it.
Are the drinks okay?
Are we gonna do stuff or not?
Wait, guys, they're--
I feel like I'm at a party.
Okay, let's go. It's on.
Thankfully Bérengère's there,
because I get the impression
Thomas doesn't really realize
where he's landed.
These stairs are the perfect place
to hum Breton songs.
Poulpe! Bérengère!
- Thomas?
- What's going on?
Did you see an entity?
- Did you see something or not?
- Fuck!
This is exactly the type of couch
I'm looking for for my place.
- You scared me!
- I went to all the flea markets.
They're there, sitting, comfortable...
It's like meringue, except you sit on it.
But we have a ghost to contact, guys!
Come on.
Let's get going with the divining rods.
Hello, Jean Saint-Clar.
My name is Thomas.
And I know you did something not so nice.
If I understand correctly,
you actually walled in your wife.
Once again, I'm not here to burden you.
I've done some stupid stuff.
Do you want a hot dog?
No.
I could understand that you feel guilty,
with respect to walling in...
people. That's not something people do,
even in this day in age.
Thomas, I wanted to let you know
I'm eating a hot dog.
I put some ketchup, mustard,
and fried onions on it,
and it's hot.
Do either of you want
to come take my place?
- Because I don't think this is working.
- Okay, I'm coming.
Yeah, right. It's not working.
It's mostly that the call of the hot dog
is stronger than the spirits.
So, you made me a hot dog?
- You told me no.
- I'm gonna go make one.
Is there an entity in the room?
I feel cold here.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
That wasn't a fart, okay? It was this.
If yes, cross the rods.
If no, separate them.
Go on, cross the rods, yeah.
Okay, you're there. I feel it.
Okay, great.
I'm gonna ask you some questions now.
Am I actually talking to Jean Saint-Clar?
Cross for yes, separate for no.
Is that you, Jean Saint-Clar?
You're separating them. It's not you.
I'm not talking to Jean Saint-Clar.
Some really weird stuff is going on.
My arms are super cold.
So, I'm talking to someone else.
Yeah, I don't feel well. I'm super hot.
I'm really hot. Is this Thérèse?
Thérèse, if that's you,
can you cross the rods?
Okay, Thérèse is here.
Okay.
Thérèse, I'm exhausted.
I don't feel well at all.
- Are you okay?
- I don't feel well.
I started to feel dizzy.
- You felt it was too much?
- I started to have crazy hot flashes.
- A hot flash?
- A big hot flash.
- And my legs were like jelly.
- Like jelly?
I think I got really stressed.
Okay, let's take a deep breath.
Let's pull ourselves together
and stay focused,
because it seems like Thérèse's spirit
is in the area.
I said to stay focused!
THREE HOURS AND 45 MINUTES BEFORE DAWN
"As punishment for adultery, Thérèse
de Saint-Clar was locked up for 15 years
in the north tower by her husband.
This room was her final resting place
after she was walled in once she died.
Bérengère is going alone to the cell
where she was imprisoned
to recreate the conditions
Thérèse experienced."
Yeah, a real nice evening for you.
The dungeon.
MISSION TWO
THE DUNGEON
Okay, guys, you have to stay focused,
because this is where Thérèse
was imprisoned for 15 years
and then walled in.
Poulpe accompanies Bérengère
to lock her up,
and Thomas...
Where is Thomas?
Fuck!
- I found this awful thing.
- I was so scared.
This is from that time.
- Bye, Bérenge.
- Bye.
Poulpe, the image of you leaving
Bérengère alone in that room...
- Enjoy your vacation.
- Thanks.
I really can't lose the key,
because it'd be a problem if...
Shit.
Let's go. With the help of her spirit box,
which captures ghosts' voices
between two FM frequencies,
Bérengère is going to try to communicate
with the spirit of poor Thérèse...
whose corpse is right in front of her...
in the dungeon wall.
Thérèse, do you wish
to communicate with me?
Is there...
someone here with me?
Wow. It looks like Thérèse
is trying to communicate.
So now's the time to take notes
and to not mess around.
I'm really good at reading lips.
- Really?
- Now she's saying...
Damn, that's impressive.
Are they serious right now?
You can use the radio
to communicate with me.
Kebab.
- Kebab.
- Samurai sauce.
Thérèse, are you there?
- Did that move?
- We've been abandoned.
ONE HOUR 45 MINUTES BEFORE DAWN
Yeah, we've been abandoned.
At the same time, you can't mess around.
If I were in Thérèse's shoes,
I would've left too,
because when it comes to playing pool
and hitting the mini bar,
you guys do it up.
Are the drinks okay?
But when it comes to contacting spirits,
after two minutes, no one's around.
I don't feel well at all.
As for who's the biggest chicken...
Thomas, I just wanted to tell you
I'm eating a hot dog.
...I don't even want talk about it.
So now, let's free Bérengère...
- Well done.
- ...and we're gonna get a lesson.
Guys, I'll be back.
There's some shit in the attic.
To contact Thérèse,
who, let me remind you,
was imprisoned for 15 years
before being walled in,
we're gonna use
the good old pedestal table in the attic.
And to do it seriously,
we're getting an expert on the matter,
Sandy Lakdar,
paranormal investigator.
Here it is. I think there's...
I feel like we misbehaved.
Yeah, we're gonna be grounded.
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah, great.
We're gonna try to do a real seance.
- Are you ready to try?
- Totally ready.
Okay. First, we're gonna
turn off the lights.
I ask all the energies in the universe
to intervene
for the nicest communication possible.
We do not want to work
with the lower astral realm.
Gabriel, I call on you to protect us
and create a protective bubble for us.
Thank you for creating
the nicest communication,
full of peace, love, and light.
Gabriel, I'm counting on you. Thank you.
May the energies of Château de Puymartin
come to us.
We're filled with love, peace, and light.
All the lords of Puymartin,
Thérèse de Saint-Clar,
we're here to listen to you, to hear you.
Please communicate with us.
I don't know if you feel it,
but there's a cold wind in here now.
I'm freezing.
- Yeah, I feel cold, too.
- Yeah, a cold wind.
I think I can feel what Thérèse feels.
Let it out. Don't hold back your feelings.
Thérèse is very sad, actually.
- Are you gonna be okay?
- Yes.
- She's using you as her medium.
- I know.
She can't talk.
Her throat is really blocked.
Together, we're gonna send
love, peace, and light to Thérèse.
She's using Bérengère.
It's gonna make her feel better.
How do you feel, Bérengère? Better?
I feel good, yes.
There you go!
That's a successful paranormal mission.
Good job, everyone.
Now let's say goodbye to Thérèse.
Listen, Thérèse, no matter what happens,
we came to cheer Puymartin up.
So, we did what we could...
We'll leave you a little mustard
and sausage downstairs
so you can make some hot dogs.
And I left
some ghost hot dogs on the stairs.
There you have it.
And the sun is rising
over Château de Puymartin.
I got my yellow belt...
- Yeah.
- ...in judo.
And I didn't see the point of--
- Idiot!
- I can't let you say that.
It wasn't judo. It was Taekwondo.
- I was so scared.
- That blood-curdling scream.
What an asshole!
Anyway, it's time to decide
who was the biggest chicken
and make them endure a punishment.
I don't know about you, but I...
I have to leave.
- I have some errands to run.
- What do you mean, errands to run?
No one's going anywhere.
First the punishment, and then we leave.
- Goodbye. Thank you.
- Goodbye, Thérèse. Good bye, everyone.
Hey, there are rules!
Come back!
Close the door. Don't let the ghosts in.
Guys, come back!
I learned something.
From now on, if someone cheats on me,
I won't wall in my woman.