A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
What's happening?
Three comedians.
Mr. and Mrs. Frotier...
- Have a son?
- What's his name?
A haunted place.
Paranormal missions.
Alice, are you with us?
Traps.
Where is Jason?
That's true. Where is Jason?
Challenges.
- I dare you.
- Listen. I accept.
We don't dare...
For the most scared...
a punishment.
Sorry. A punishment.
A game...
that will last...
until dawn.
SOMEWHERE IN LA VIENNE...
- Whose ghost would you like to see?
- Joan of Arc's.
Tupac's.
I think Zidane's,
even though he's not dead.
He's so great
that his ghost is already here.
So... "Your destination is
the Château de Fougeret,
one of the most haunted places in France."
Fougeret, a very old castle
from the Middle Ages
with towers that make people freak out,
windows that make people freak out,
hallways that make people freak out...
In short, it will make you
totally freak out.
I didn't tell you
about the ghosts of the old owners.
Yes, they still occupy
the rooms and everything.
Really. Well, there you go.
"A young girl with a tragic destiny.
A couple buried at the bottom of a crypt.
- Stillborns."
- That's not good.
"So many ghosts that you'll no doubt
cross one's path tonight."
- Weird. I'm starting to not feel well.
- I'm sure I won't make it.
I'm playing it cool now, but I think...
in an hour, I'll be in tears,
calling for my mother.
Yeah, if you have phone service,
given the place...
I doubt it!
MIDNIGHT - SIX HOURS BEFORE DAWN
I can't see anything. Bismillah.
Tonight, the goal of the game
is to face your fears...
If I see something sketchy,
I'm gonna abandon my teammates.
And play with the others.
I believe in spirits.
It's better to annoy Tania and Hakim.
I prefer pissing them off
over the spirits.
At dawn, our three friends
will decide who was the most scared.
And for that person, a prize...
the...
punishment!
Yeah, that's it. That's what we said.
I think Hakim is a real chicken,
so I'm putting all my eggs in that basket.
- I see the castle.
- Shit!
Something definitely lives there.
Yeah, fuck.
- Are you ready?
- Let's go. Bismillah.
Okay, welcome to the house of crazies.
Inside, surveillance cameras,
three floors,
20 rooms that have been uninhabited
since last century,
antique decor,
all very scary.
- Where is Jason?
- That asshole.
Fuck, get your light.
- I'm not letting go of you.
- Okay. Where's Jason?
No...
From the start, man!
Actually, we entered the house,
and I left straightaway. I left them.
And they're panicking
since they didn't see me leave.
Jason's hiding out on the second floor.
Tania and Hakim are still looking for him
on the first floor.
Fortunately, we can count on Tania
to stay calm.
- Did you hear that?
- Fuck!
They're panicking.
- Where was it?
- It was up there.
Go. He's up there.
That asshole is hiding somewhere for sure.
Wait, don't move.
Did you hear that?
I didn't see that doll. Fuck.
It wasn't there before.
It wasn't there before, was it?
Were you there before or not?
It's horrible. God forgive us.
Wait. No, wait.
Wait, Tania. Stay with me.
You're such an asshole!
Man, you went too far.
That's not cool, seriously. You're gonna
pay. I won't let you off easy.
FIVE HOURS AND 12 MINUTES
BEFORE DAWN
Jason started the animosity
for tonight's competition.
In order to chase ghosts,
the trio has a headquarters.
They have
all the necessary equipment there
for their paranormal missions,
such as surveillance monitors,
walkie-talkies, etc.
Okay, guys.
So... "Mission one: the crypt." Fuck.
This is starting off well.
"Château de Fougeret's crypt is buried
tens of meters below the surface.
It has served as a tomb for centuries."
Fuck. There must be 10,000 dead.
"You can particularly get in contact
with Mr. and Mrs. Frotier,
who were some of the castle's
first owners.
They've haunted the crypt for centuries.
Goal of the mission:
go into the depths of the castle alone
and get in contact
with its first occupants.
The chosen one: Tania Dutel.
Take your flashlight and two pods."
That's you!
Frankly, I swear that's not cool.
What are pods?
Pods:
presence detectors that flash and beep
before a ghost.
There you go. Like that.
Everyone take a walkie-talkie
to communicate. Here, Tania.
- How do I know where the crypt is?
- It's there. Look.
"Hall" and there's a staircase there.
MISSION ONE
THE FROTIER CRYPT
- Can you hear us?
- No, there's static.
Go down.
Honestly, it's gonna be hard
to do what she's doing.
Well, I'm in the dark.
To contact the Frotier couple,
you have to put the pods on the ground.
But the best way to get the spirits
to come is in the dark.
- Tania?
- Tania, turn the light off.
No!
- No, fuck!
- There are rules!
Can I light a candle for light?
- Do you have a lighter?
- There are matches.
- Yeah, go ahead. Light the candle.
- Yeah.
Shit.
It's okay. Take you're time.
- Take your time. Stay calm.
- This is ridiculous.
Okay.
- Mr. and Mrs. Frotier...
- Have a son.
What's his name?
I have no ill intentions towards you.
I love ghosts,
and I'd be super happy
if we could talk.
So, I'm honestly not here to bother you.
I swear.
My friends are up there watching.
So, there you go. Are we welcome
or do you want us to run away?
Tania? We have to turn off
the walkie-talkies, okay?
- No!
- We see you. Listen!
They'll be more likely to make contact
if we turn them off.
Once those are off,
you must blow out the candle.
No, I don't want to do that!
Don't worry.
They'll understand that you're friendly.
It's just so they can appear.
You have nothing to worry about.
Everything's fine.
There can't be any radio waves.
Otherwise, it won't work.
- Come on. See you soon.
- Okay.
Friendship.
Mr. and Mrs. Frotier,
I present myself.
Did you close it? No?
- Yes.
- Shit!
What else can I tell you?
I have an older sister and two brothers.
And so...
Well, they're nice.
Do you want us to leave,
Mr. and Mrs. Frotier?
What's happening?
Leave, Tania.
No!
What's happening?
Fuck...
- Is the gate closed?
- Yes.
Shit!
As if you didn't know!
Fuck.
Go, Tania. Get out!
- I'm completely serious. Hurry.
- Stop!
FOUR HOURS AND SIX MINUTES
BEFORE DAWN
- First contact in the crypt.
- Success.
Well, success...
to be determined
since the beeps said, "Leave."
Well, we've lasted the night.
We're not quitting now.
- Did you see what happened?
- It was too far. How'd you do it?
- You told the ghosts your life story.
- I was trying to...
- Honestly, I was scared.
- Locking the gate went too far.
- Did you do that?
- No, it was Mrs. Frotier.
- I kind of know her.
- Right.
And now for the "beep beep."
Yes, it's a "beep beep."
- And the false imprisonment...
- No!
Jason and Hakim are off to a good start.
If Tania doesn't get moving,
she risks losing.
I'm so gonna get back at them.
It's gonna be crazy.
At the start of the night,
Hakim showed Tania something
that rubbed him wrong.
I didn't see that doll. Fuck.
It wasn't there before.
It wasn't there before, was it?
Yeah, dolls aren't Hakim's thing.
And it's funny,
because on the second floor,
there's this room.
- Hakim?
- Yeah?
You locked me downstairs. So now,
you will have to go into the doll room
and do a show in front of the dolls
while we watch from here.
Can you do it or not?
Listen, I think I can do it.
- I can do it.
- Go on. Improvise for us.
And I want to laugh.
VENGEANCE
Fuck, this is freaky.
I have to do a show in front of the dolls.
To be honest, I'm not happy.
I don't know how it's gonna go.
I'm really freaking out.
Imagine if the dolls laugh.
Ladies and gentle-dolls, good evening.
Welcome to the Hakim Jemili Show.
We'll start by clapping a shitload...
for Mr. Hakim Jemili!
Good evening.
Are there any doll couples?
First dig.
I'm going to scare him.
- Fuck!
- Hello, dolly.
Hello, you.
Your dress is beautiful!
Are you the gold-digger doll?
Is that it?
Hello, little doll.
Well, you...
You're seated. You're good.
You're watching the show quietly.
Why is her mouth so open?
Hakim is in the doll room.
He's doing a show.
I know this. The rhythm's missing.
I'm gonna add a little rhythm to his show.
I'm gonna scare the shit out of him.
Today, I'm gonna present
two of your friends,
who you know.
Here. To my left, Adeline.
To my right...
Fuck, this fucking one is scary!
Fuck!
He had a heart attack!
Doll: one...
Jason: one.
Hakim: zero.
Judging who's the winner
is getting hard, Hakim.
At this rate, we're gonna wake people up.
- Obviously.
- Are you coming?
Are we doing another mission
or do we keep going?
THREE HOURS AND 18 MINUTES
BEFORE DAWN
"The room of the masters
is the biggest room in the castle.
The owner's wife
had several miscarriages there.
Numerous paranormal occurrences
have been observed in the past,
notably recordings of a baby crying.
Jason's mission:
pick up these paranormal noises.
If contact is effective,
it should calm the spirits of the babies.
But maybe he'll be the one
who needs reassurance...
because Jason doesn't seem his best.
It's really starting to get dark here.
MISSION TWO
ROOM OF THE MASTERS
Okay, kids, it's your uncle.
We don't know each other,
but rest assured...
It'll be all right, okay?
Everything's all right.
The technique for picking up
the baby spirits' cries
involves placing a baby monitor
in the crib...
and then leaving quietly.
- Jason, did you hear something?
- I don't hear anything.
Be patient. Like those who come
to see your shows.
At least people come to see me.
No paranormal activity at the moment.
Tania?
A little vengeance, no?
I just got out the baby monitor,
and I'm gonna start making baby noises.
They're real noises
and you'll be a little scared.
Yes, since Tania
took the second baby monitor
from Jason's bag.
Little devil.
- I hear them crying.
- You hear them?
There are some weird noises.
I don't know if they're babies or what,
but there are weird sounds.
Like I said, I absolutely don't want
to look for spirits, babies or adults.
- I don't hear anything now.
- Okay.
I'm sure there are noises.
I don't know where they're coming from,
but they're there. I'm leaving quietly.
For a guy who was supposed to reassure
the spirits of the babies,
I feel like saying, "Well done, champion."
ONE HOUR AND 43 MINUTES
BEFORE DAWN
The night goes on and so does
the competition. Tania isn't very hungry.
- Cake?
- No, thanks.
I told you.
And she knows that at dawn,
a punishment awaits the most scared.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
The story...
"Alice was the niece of one
of the owners of the castle.
She was part of the jeunesse dorée
during the 1920s
and always vacationed at Fougeret.
In July of 1924, she fell seriously ill
from a respiratory infection
and died at age 22.
Her body was taken to her room
at Fougeret to be looked after.
Ever since,
she often appears in that room.
Goal of the mission:
use the Ouija board
to get in contact with Alice."
MISSION THREE
ALICE'S ROOM
Should we get on the ground?
I think it's with two fingers,
but I don't know if we both use both hands
or just one each.
First let's reassure her
by saying that we're here to...
What are we doing?
We're gonna talk to her.
So we're gonna say, "Alice...
are we welcome in your bedroom?"
Don't push it, guys.
- We're not.
- Okay.
Alice, if you hear us, are you here?
Alice, if you hear us...
tell us you're here in the room.
Is our presence bothering you, Alice?
I'm starting to feel weird.
My heart's beating like crazy.
I swear.
I've had a feeling
in the pit of my stomach from earlier.
- Because you ate too much.
- No, it's not...
It's in my rib cage.
Tania? What's going on?
- What's up with you?
- Are you okay?
What's up?
Hey, Tania, what's up with you?
- You're freaking me out!
- Tania, careful.
Tania.
- Hey, hey.
- Take it slow.
Hey, hey.
Look at me! Look at me, Tania.
Look at me!
Tania! Stop crying!
Calm down. We're here.
Calm down.
It's Jason. Everything's fine.
- I know.
- Fuck! Fucking shit.
Okay.
All right. That's done.
Alice, if you hear us...
Are you with us in this room?
Alice, show yourself one way or another.
Alice...
My God!
Come on. Let's get out of here.
Fuck! What happened?
I will never set foot in that room again.
Guys, what happened was crazy.
The noises made me freak out. I swear.
And the thing moved. Holy shit.
16 MINUTES BEFORE DAWN
The sun is rising
over Château de Fougeret.
It's time for Tania, Hakim, and Jason
to decide who was
the most scared last night
and make that person endure...
the punishment!
So who, what, when?
The time is now!
- What's the punishment?
- The crypt.
The crypt.
The only thing is
that I did the crypt alone,
in the dark.
If anyone deserves to see the sun rise...
- No, really...
- I can't leave Tania.
I won't leave without her.
So you're gonna have to stay.
- I have to stay?
- Yeah.
I won't leave without Tania either.
No one wants to go into the crypt.
Overall, if we recap the night...
Tania freaked out.
Hakim freaked out.
Jason freaked out.
In short, all three freaked out.
What do we do in the case of a tie?
All three of us go, guys!
- Come on. Let's go.
- Are you coming with us?
Yes, I'm gonna go with you.
THE PUNISHMENT
Fuck, that's scary.
- Come with me.
- Don't worry. I swear...
I'm a friend.
You went down there?
- Further down?
- Yeah, I went down there, guys.
You did that alone?
- Yeah, I did it alone.
- You're completely insane.
- I did this all alone, guys.
- It's crazy slippery.
- You're a trooper to have gone alone.
- Did you see?
I wouldn't have done it alone.
I'll tell you that.
Hakim, you locked me in earlier.
Tania, we didn't vote against you.
Fuck! Open up!
Tania, that's not funny! The key!
Tania!
I think we can say that I won.
Are there mice on the ground?
- Are those edible?
- You'd really have to be hungry.
Tania!