A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
Let's pretend this is a nice
and super pleasant visit.
There's a guy over there...
Three comedians.
It's your turn to see
if you can contact those spirits
to see if they're still suffering.
Even if they're still suffering,
everyone has their problems.
A haunted place.
Paranormal missions.
Are you there?
It's working! I don't like this!
Traps.
Challenges.
You have to do something horrible.
Turn everything off.
Fuck...
I'm not okay! Motherf--
For the biggest chicken...
I swear to God.
...a punishment.
I wanna go home to my mom.
A game that's going to last...
If you're hungry,
I'll make you a tarte tatin.
...until dawn.
SOMEWHERE IN THE PYRENEES...
- It's made of stone.
- Very Middle Ages.
- This is old stone.
- A medieval village.
- Yeah, it's very Middle Ages.
- There's a cat!
- That's a bad omen.
- You have to take me back to the hotel.
It's not reassuring.
- I'm filming the street.
- Jhon thinks he's Stanley Kubrick!
I'm a director. Leave me alone!
Tonight, the goal of the game
is to face your fears...
I don't like this. I avoid these things.
I've already been stressed out,
but this...
This is the most stressful.
...and to play
with the fears of the others.
Stop it! It's working!
The thing that could make me lose it
is feeling like I'm being touched.
That's terrible.
At dawn, they'll decide
who was the biggest chicken
and give them a punishment.
The most scared,
I really think, is Jhon.
- Fuck!
- "Underground of the fortified castle."
The two words don't go together.
"Underground" and "fortified castle."
Wait, first open the letter.
"At the end of the staircase,
you will enter Fort Liberia."
Fort Liberia.
When it comes to creepy spots,
this place is perfect.
In this 17th-century prison,
a vast network of female poisoners
was locked up
under Louis XIV's orders.
"Condemned to silence, the prisoners-- "
I don't like this.
"...would stay there until death.
This building was also
the scene of bloody attacks
which left traces."
What craziness.
In any case,
between the spirits of the Sun King
and those of the female murderers
adept at black magic,
when it comes to ghosts,
this sounds like a promising group.
"It seems that at nightfall
the souls reclaim
- the premises."
- Of course.
- I don't wanna listen.
- "The feeling of being watched,
sounds of crying..."
- No.
- There you go.
"Climb the stairs
and you'll find your headquarters
to start your investigation.
Who will be the most scared?"
MIDNIGHT - SIX HOURS BEFORE DAWN
Stop! Listen!
Look how long the hallway
and the staircase are.
It goes on forever.
I'm out of breath.
- I...
- What's that behind you?
- Stop!
- I swear. What the hell?
- What did you see?
- We don't see anything.
- Damn it.
- Shine your light.
All good.
Day 367. We're still on the stairs.
The year is 2023.
- What's this?
- Fuck!
An eagle!
Stop! I swear. I don't like birds.
Come here. Go behind me.
Look how big it is!
Why is it looking at me like that?
Don't touch me!
See? When I try to pass, it's screeches!
- Holy shit.
- Are you okay, bro?
The Pyrenees eagle.
No surprise.
The fort is located at 600 meters high.
From up there, no one hears them screech.
Stop!
- I swear to God, there's a body.
- Wait.
Look, there's a body.
- What?
- Look, there's a body.
What's that? Look in my camera.
- Fuck!
- What is that?
- Look, I'm filming. What is that?
- Okay.
- What's that?
- It's a mannequin.
Yeah, I forgot.
This former prison turned museum
is filled with 100 mannequins
just to spice things up a little.
- That's your bag!
- My purse.
Listen, this is gloomy.
HQ is cool. Check it out.
- There's a witch tree.
- HQ is the most reassuring.
Headquarters.
Equipment, surveillance cameras,
monitoring screens...
Everything they need is here
to complete their paranormal missions
for this nighttime competition.
Jeanfi, it's on!
"A few years ago,
some paranormal experts
assure they found the Sun King's ghost..."
I don't give a fuck.
I don't wanna see him.
"...near the chapel...
- Jhon Rachid..."
- No!
"...you're going to try
to make contact with his ghost
to understand why he didn't behead
the female poisoners."
- I don't wanna go.
- It'll be all right.
"Go look for the keys
in building number two,
box number two."
What the hell?
Why is it always the chapel?
MISSION ONE
THE SUN KING'S SPIRIT
Climb the stairs to the third level.
- Fuck!
- Holy shit.
Go up the stairs.
There are noises, I swear to God.
Well, between us,
the chapel door isn't really locked.
Since Jhon's going for the keys, it gives
his buddies time to prank him.
- Right, Audrey?
- I have an idea. I'll be back.
Jhon, sorry,
but this prank is too tempting.
My friend, you know
I'm doing this out of pure love
and pure fun.
I'm going inside that chapel.
And forgive me.
You should see the keys in box number two.
Okay, I got one.
There you go. You have to come back down.
We can stop there.
I'm already freaked out.
- Jeanfi, stay with me.
- I'm here.
Where's Audrey?
She's in the bathroom.
I'm going to God's house,
like we say back home.
So, I inserted the key...
Yeah, that's generally what you do
to open a door.
I'm turning it.
Holy fucking shit!
There are people inside.
They're praying. It's a chapel.
This is bullshit.
Okay. What's this? Okay.
Salaam alaikum, Louis XIV.
Holy fucking shit. Hold on!
Okay, I come in peace.
I'm a super cool dude.
If you're not cool with me,
I have a stick.
I will fuck you up.
I could stab someone
with these divining rods.
Yeah, however, the rods, above all,
allow you to communicate with the spirits.
So let's sit down and chill out.
So, Louis XIV, I come in peace.
I bring good vibes.
We can dance to funk or do what your want.
There's no bad energy, nothing.
I'm really chilled out.
I'm France's coolest guy.
So, I'm gonna establish
what "yes" and "no" are.
For "yes", separate the rods.
For "no", cross them.
Are you there?
Motherfucker, it's working!
I don't like this.
It's working. They separated.
I didn't touch them. They separated.
I told you I don't like this.
Louis XIV, bro,
why are you angry?
If it's because we're here,
separate the rods.
If it's because you got your shit going on
that's stressing you out a little
and you need a shrink or whatever,
cross the rods.
Those aren't questions, Jhon Rachid.
Ask him if he's angry at...
Jeanfi, please, let's think about this.
I'm in the middle of a chapel
with a group of people around me.
Fuck, the more I look at them,
the more they freak me out.
Come on.
So, Louis XIV, why didn't you execute
the women of the prison?
You can't--
You can't respond yes or no?
I heard some noise.
I'm gonna come closer.
Don't move.
You don't move either.
You there, you're weird.
You, there you go.
Stop it!
It's me.
I can't breathe. I swear to God.
Feel this.
Laugh, but feel this.
Audrey, you motherfucker.
That's awful.
Fuck, I should have known
from the beginning.
Fuck.
Audrey's prank worked,
and Jhon Rachid needs to be careful
because at dawn, a punishment
awaits the biggest chicken.
But the competition between our three pals
is far from over.
FOUR HOURS AND 30 MINUTES BEFORE DAWN
"In the 17th century,
one of the prisons
was reserved for women.
They were all sentenced to life
for participating
in different black masses
and several murders using lethal poisons.
Anne Guesdon and La Chapelain
stayed until age 36 and 43 respectively
between these walls
for the attempted murder of Louis XIV.
However, they claimed their innocence
until the end.
Ever since they died in their cell,
they continue to haunt the place.
Audrey, it's up to you
to make contact with them
and to figure out
if they're really guilty."
MISSION TWO
THE LADIES' PRISON
- It'll be okay!
- Yeah.
Lord, poor girl.
Off to the prison alone to contact
the ghosts of the female poisoners
Anne de Guesdon and La Chapelain.
Fortunately, thanks to the walkie-talkies,
Audrey isn't really alone.
Talk to us, Audrey. You're not alone.
- Audrey!
- Do you hear us?
Shit! I can barely hear them.
- Fuck, we can't hear her anymore.
- Yeah...
Actually, she is alone.
There we go.
I can't hear you anymore. I'm telling you.
- But not exactly alone.
- Motherfucker.
No! No!
Yes, yes, yes.
And now, if there's a spirit nearby,
a weird noise could come out of nowhere
or sound the presence detector
Audrey's placing on the floor.
You're in position.
I'm switching you on.
But in order to lure the poisoner's souls,
Audrey has to relive
their past behind bars.
That means locking the door
and throwing the key away.
My God.
She's in the dark, locked in a cell.
I'm...
Audrey.
I came to you...
in order to...
see if you're here in this place.
Could you show yourself
with the little thingy, please?
Fucking motherfucker.
It seems like one is turning its head
towards me.
No!
I'm scared.
First, let me ask Anne Guesdon...
and La Chapelain...
to show yourselves.
We really didn't bring a--
I swear to God!
The poor thing!
No, that's too scary.
Boys, can you come
and help me, please?
'Cause, let me remind you,
I threw away the key
- Do you wanna go?
- I'm going.
Yeah, well, that's true. Locking
yourself in and throwing away the key...
maybe wasn't the best idea in the world.
It smells like shit.
Fuck!
- Where did you throw the key?
- I threw it over there, by your feet.
Fuck!
Bats!
- Go away!
No, what a nightmare!
Shh, don't move. Slowly...
Damn!
My God!
In this competition
for the biggest chicken,
Jhon Rachid can thank the bats
for scaring his buddies.
TWO HOURS AND 15 MINUTES BEFORE DAWN
But Jeanfi plans to turn things around
with a good scary story.
One time...
I was in Les Landes at a friend's house,
and his mother passed away.
He buried her ashes
at the foot of a pine tree,
'cause she liked stone pines.
And one windy day,
listen closely,
the house we were at started burning down.
- No.
- Yes.
'Cause of a short circuit,
everything burned,
except the mother's room,
- which is next to the stone pine.
- No!
And when I say everything, I mean
everything was black, turned to ashes,
except the mother's room was intact.
Fuck!
No.
Yes!
Motherfucker!
- It's an eagle!
- Stop!
Let's get out of here.
The chicken attack
was not part of the plan,
but it made the story
so much more effective
that even Jeanfi freaked out.
I need to drop the kids off at the pool.
I'm gonna go shit.
And then me.
But if he wants to get out
of the punishment,
he's gonna have to keep his cool
during the last paranormal mission.
"Fort Liberia is particularly isolated..."
We didn't notice.
"At the time, the soldiers who stayed
were treated on site
in precarious conditions,
and many of them died
in excruciating pain from infections.
- Jeanfi..." That's me.
- No!
"It's your turn to see
if you can make contact with these spirits
and find out if they're still suffering."
Even if they're still suffering,
everyone has their problems.
- Jeanfi, it's your turn to go.
- Wait, where is it?
You have to go up the stairs
and it'll be there.
Jeanfi, you need to take
the pendulum on the shelf.
- The what?
- The pendulum.
Despite the name,
this pendulum doesn't tell time.
However, it might indicate
if a ghost has an opinion.
In short, for "yes," the spirits
will make the ball turn right,
and to say "no," left.
- Wait, you need a flashlight too.
- Wait.
My mother didn't give birth to an octopus.
I only have two arms.
- Put the pendulum in your pocket.
- I gotta take it out if there's a monster.
- There are no monsters.
- Fuck, I'm not well.
- I'm staying here.
- I hate this.
I hope I won't cry when I see you leave.
MISSION THREE
THE MILITARY HOSPITAL
Poor thing.
Fuck!
I'm fucking dying right now!
I think I'm here.
I swear, I'm really gonna freak out, guys.
There's a staircase.
Another staircase. Fuck!
You're near the nursery. Don't be scared.
It'll be on your right.
Go to your right. Right there...
Fuck!
- Over there too! Look! Horrible.
- She has her back to him.
- I swear to God, this is horrible.
- So...
It seems soldiers
are getting treated here.
You have to use the pendulum
and tell them that to say "yes,"
they need to swing it clockwise,
and to say "no," counter-clockwise.
I'm not well. Son of a bitch.
I am not well.
Yeah, well, you haven't seen anything yet.
Soon you won't see anything,
because if you want to pick up
the spirits' strange noises...
- Fuck.
- ...you have to do it in the dark.
- Fuck!
- Turn off your light.
No!
Sir.
No, I'm a friend.
Fuck!
Please, I'm just here
to understand your suffering
and to help you. I want to help you.
Poor thing.
Do you hear me?
I can help you.
Can I help you in any way?
"Yes."
The thing is turning.
He's not okay.
He's gonna puke.
I'm gonna lay down next to you,
right here,
in order to feel your pain
and see what treatment I can give you.
Everything's okay.
Hey? Everything's okay. Well, not for you.
I'm gonna help you.
I'm trying to feel what you feel.
I'm gonna prank Jeanfi.
Fuck!
What a scare!
There were some fucking crazy noises...
We saw you on the monitor.
We couldn't stand it. Sorry, Jeanfi.
The sun is rising over Fort Liberia.
It's time for Audrey,
Jhon,
and Jeanfi
to decide who was the biggest chicken
and make them suffer the punishment.
Okay, so who's the biggest chicken?
It's a tie.
I think so.
Audrey was the strongest.
It's between you and us.
- "You and us."
- Yeah, I'm still in this.
- I had the chapel.
- Yeah, we saw.
Motherfucker, it's working!
I don't like this.
- And the hospital?
- We saw that too.
Fuck!
We mostly heard that.
And on the scream scale...
- Motherfucker! Stop!
- ...there's no comparison.
- You're the biggest chicken.
- I can't do this again. I've had enough.
- Jeanfi, please.
- I have an idea.
And it's to help you demystify the chapel.
Don't be a bitch, Jeanfi.
No, that's okay...
THE PUNISHMENT
They're just gonna lock you
in the place you like the least,
where your buddy is, Louis XIV.
- Stop!
- Close it!
- Bye!
- You're not my sister anymore. It's over.
I know. It's terrible.
- I love you.
- I swear to God.
- Come on. Let's go.
- Leave me a flashlight.
- Kisses, my friend.
- Bye!
Leave me a flashlight!
No, I swear to God!
Come back! That's enough. I did it.
It's dawn!
Do you have your stuff?
I'm not coming back.
Come on!
Come on! That's enough!