A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
Stop!
Fuck! Shut up!
Three comedians.
It was my shadow. I was scared.
A haunted place.
Paranormal missions.
Is the treasure in one of these rooms?
Traps.
Stop!
Challenges.
- There's an armchair. Sit in it.
- No!
For the most scared...
a punishment!
A game that's going to last...
until dawn.
Lord.
I have no idea where we're going.
- Me neither.
- What's the worst that could happen?
SOMEWHERE IN BURGUNDY...
- The worst?
- Yeah.
That someone chases us.
Stop! Stop, already!
The minute you say something,
I get freaked out.
- Stop. Don't laugh.
- Anne-So, you're lying.
- Are you scared of anything specific?
- I don't like insects.
I'm pretending everything's fine.
I don't watch horror films.
What am I doing here?
I don't know.
Guigui's waiting for us over there.
Careful.
- Yeah, but he must not be okay.
- What's that?
He'll pretend to be, but he's not.
So, wait. Where are we?
Okay.
Okay. Well...
I hope my friends don't take too long
because I'm already shitting my pants.
Okay, friends.
I'm the first to arrive.
I'm gonna hide in the armoire over there.
And I'm gonna give them a little scare
to welcome them.
Guillaume is going all out!
No surprise, because the goal
of tonight's game is to face your fears
and to play with the others' fears.
- Who do you think will be the most scared?
- I think it'll be you!
I'm such a chicken. I admit it.
It's not...
But I would like-- Fuck.
At dawn, a punishment
awaits the biggest chicken.
I'm gonna give my all
to avoid the punishment.
We haven't gotten inside yet.
This is still the path to the castle.
- Okay, I was expecting a chapel.
- Yeah, definitely.
No... It's enormous!
Yes, it's huge.
And it's called
the Manor of the Chastenay.
It's from the 14th century,
and it's built
over a network of scary caves.
- No, I'm gonna freak out.
- No!
But the scariest part is
there's a treasure here
that was hidden by a bloodthirsty duke.
Excuse me.
I think there are enough horror films
that start with a blond girl, a black guy,
and a disabled man in a haunted house.
- And here we are!
- I swear, here we are.
It's really big. So, wait.
Come. There's light.
We're gonna go inside.
This must be the headquarters.
I'm already super happy
to have made it here.
- Guigui!
- Good. We can turn off our flashlights.
Gui?
- Guigui, you asshole.
- There you go.
- Guigui, you're not serious.
- Okay, great.
You're such an idiot.
You're really gonna pay. You'll see.
They're already talking about revenge
and the missions haven't even started yet.
At HQ, there's all the equipment needed
in the search for this treasure
protected by the evil duke's spirit,
which will end... at dawn.
MIDNIGHT - SIX HOURS BEFORE DAWN
So... "Elhadj,
it's time to go meet the duke."
- Why do I have to go first?
- Listen.
It's always like that, actually.
- The black guy's always first.
- You'll have to go to the cellar
with the pendulum. Where is it?
The pendulum...
A little dangling ball
that will be used to communicate
with the spirit of the duke,
who's actually not that nice of a guy.
"Each person suspected
of knowing where the treasure was
became a potential target.
In his craziness, the duke
physically mutilated his servants.
A presence still haunts the cellar.
Try to establish a dialogue
with this presence
to find out if it's really the duke."
No, I'm laughing,
- but it's not funny at all.
- I'm glad I'm not going. Sorry.
Deep down, I want to die.
MISSION ONE
THE DUKE'S CELLAR
No. Why me first and not the others?
Go on. We're with you.
I swear, I'm not well.
So, damn.
Well...
My God!
Fuck!
- What? What is it?
- You're not serious.
Stop. We're talking.
So, I was saying I prefer it in gray.
No, keep playing. You'll see.
- ...the color taupe...
- Keep screaming.
Thanks to Guillaume and Anne-So,
who's touching up her makeup,
Elhadj isn't very calm.
And he hasn't seen the cellar yet.
- No!
- What is it?
The stairs are very narrow,
and I'm gonna take them to the cellar?
Have you seen me?
I'm starting to panic.
I'm claustrophobic.
I hope downstairs is...
No, don't be scared.
You're not serious! I swear.
- Hello?
- Yes.
- We're proud of you.
- Yeah.
Honestly, it's cool.
Keeping going. You're getting there.
I stepped in-- What is that thing?
- Frogs.
- Fuck!
Then again, I did warn you
that the manor was built
on top of a very humid cave.
But no one ever listens to me.
Shit!
Yeah, well, the scariest part
will be sitting in this armchair
and contacting the duke's spirit
to find out where his treasure is hidden.
But it's dirty! There's dust all over it.
I'm gonna...
No, I don't wanna do this.
I'm gonna go crazy.
What's that noise?
My God!
Why?
Is there anyone...
in this place?
I'm hot, I'm cold, I'm hot, I'm cold.
Is the treasure still hidden here?
No, wait.
No, I'm gonna lose it.
Okay, I think it's moving.
You have to leave, bro.
What is this bullshit?
My heart! I have to hang in there. Sorry.
Fuck. I'm outside.
I'm outside!
I'm never touching a pendulum
again in my life. I don't want to know.
- Did you feel something?
- Like something was pulling on it.
You feel a slight force on it.
- I didn't want to insist...
- We saw it move.
We saw it move.
And if it moved, that means
the duke did hide something in the area.
To try to find it,
the night's second paranormal mission.
It has to be done fast.
FOUR HOURS BEFORE DAWN
The treasure hunt ends at dawn.
"The duke,
convinced his most loyal servant
knew where it was hidden,
locked her up in a dungeon in the attic
and cut off her tongue
so she could never speak.
Anne-Sophie, it's your turn
to contact the poor mute woman
in any way other than talking.
Go with a castle map and the planchette."
The planchette is
a mystical means of communication.
If the servant's spirit manages
to move it on the map of the manor,
we'll know where the loot is.
No, I'm gonna be all alone! This can't be.
Fuck! Stop!
MISSION TWO
THE DUNGEON
I'm not well, guys.
Fuck!
Listen, you have to go to the dungeon.
No! A dungeon? Are you crazy or what?
- This can't be.
- No!
- No.
- Yes, I swear.
In the attic, there's a little spot
and that's the dungeon.
Come on. Where is it? On my right?
On your right, Anne-So!
Motherfucker!
- What?
- No, it was my shadow.
I was scared! Fuck!
There's a stupid fucking mirror.
Fuck. I hear you laughing.
I hate you guys. I swear.
No, but why am I doing this?
Well, to contact the servant
whose tongue was cut off
to find out where the treasure is.
- Hold on a second. It's 48 degrees here.
- It's getting hot. I like it.
- Stop!
- No, that's not the mission.
- Fuck.
- I'm loving it.
Put both hands on the planchette
and start by introducing yourself
to the servant.
No kidding.
Hello.
I'm Anne-Sophie.
Sorry to bother you.
Is the treasure
hidden in one of these rooms?
The stairs...
The guards' room...
She doesn't want to talk or say anything.
Well, her tongue was cut off.
The poor woman.
Sometimes it's subtle. It can be...
a shiver...
a draft...
It won't be something sudden.
It's smooth, but every time
I go over the bakery, it slips.
I'm super hot, I swear.
I'm not well.
Motherfucker!
- What happened?
- Fuck, I saw something!
- Fuck!
- When you were on the bakery?
Okay, then. We had a lovely time.
All good things come to an end. Let's go.
TWO HOURS AND 27 MINUTES BEFORE DAWN
I'm not well!
I have a sharp pain in my side.
I'm gonna die.
You're getting on my nerves!
I'm sick of you guys.
- So?
- I'm too tired.
- The dungeon?
- No, 48 degrees in the dungeon.
- It's stifling.
- And the thing with the bakery?
It was around the bottom
of the planchette.
It wasn't something super...
- Distinct?
- No, not at all.
Actually, something
was happening there each time.
I'm exhausted.
Let's recap.
With Elhadj, we learned
the treasure was in the area.
I'm gonna lose it.
With Anne-Sophie,
the location became more precise.
Every time I go over the bakery, it slips.
Motherfucker!
So now, it's Guillaume's turn to go look
for the treasure with a thermal camera.
My God.
The thermal camera is horrible!
- You're gonna see sources of heat.
- Yeah.
It's red when it's hot,
blue when it's cold.
I got it. I've seen TV shows.
Dawn is near.
MISSION THREE
THE CURSED TREASURE
But Guillaume still has to search
the bakery to find the cursed treasure.
When his buddies were struggling,
he laughed.
I stepped in-- What is that thing?
But now we'll see
if he's still gonna be a smartass
alone in the dark.
Come on, ghosts. I don't give a fuck!
Stop! You're gonna provoke them.
Don't laugh.
You're provoking them. Fuck.
You're very rude.
I'm acting tough, like I'm not scared,
but now I'm getting scared.
I'm scared. There.
- Where am I going? What do I do?
- You have to look in zones with heat,
and you'll find something there.
I can see myself as heat in the mirror.
- Go by the oven.
- Okay.
Is there something inside?
There's the camera's heat.
- You have to see if there's something.
- There.
- Like what?
- If there's treasure or not.
- Put your head in and check.
- Something shady.
There's some wood.
- That's it?
- Nothing. You're fucking with me.
And there are no other sources of heat?
Yeah, on my left, there's an area of heat.
Hold on. I'll turn on my flashlight.
Fuck, damn. He's scary.
Look at his eyes.
Stop. Can you imagine
if the treasure were inside?
If I said there were worms on it,
- would you believe me?
- Stop!
- There are what?
- There. Look.
- Stop!
- On its feet.
- Shut up!
- Inside the fox, actually.
- Are you kidding? There are worms?
- Stop! Fuck! Sorry.
- Yeah, there are worms in it.
- Stop!
Fuck!
In my opinion,
the treasure must be inside.
- You know what? I have a good idea.
- What?
I'm gonna bring it back.
- Are you fucking with me?
- Stop playing!
- Don't do that!
- Stop the foolishness.
- See you soon.
- Stop your bullshit. Hello?
- Bro, listen.
- Too late. I'm outside, bro.
- What?
- We're gonna dissect the creature.
No, but...
- The worms were on the ground.
- No! Stop!
Don't come closer! Fuck!
I'm not joking! Stop!
- Why are you putting it by our stuff?
- Look.
What I'm gonna do is disgusting.
I'm gonna stick my hand in your body.
No, he's insane.
So... how should I put it?
We all want
to get our hands on the treasure.
But maybe this is going too far.
- Fuck!
- He's insane!
Look near the bottom.
Fuck, it's disgusting.
That's enough.
It's so disgusting it's time to stop.
Fortunately, the sun is rising, putting
an end to this hardcore treasure hunt.
Anne-So, come back.
Well, we'll never know
what's hidden in the manor...
or the fox.
Even if our three friends
couldn't get their hands
on the loot hidden by the duke,
they should be able to determine
who was the biggest chicken.
- Let's vote.
- For the biggest chicken?
I wasn't even scared.
One, two, three!
- There!
- Your punishment will be the cellar.
- No!
And we'll lock you down there.
No! Stop laughing!
THE PUNISHMENT
- No!
- Bye, Anne-Sophie.
- Go down to the cellar!
Stop. Leave the door open.
- Okay, can you go down?
- I'm going.
But don't you close the door.
No, seriously.
- Otherwise I'm gonna lose it.
- Of course.
Okay.
- Go down. Stop talking.
- Don't leave me alone.
- That wouldn't be cool.
- Go on. Go down.
Stop. No, there are frogs and everything.
- We're out of here.
- Bye-bye, we're leaving.
Fuck! Open the door!
Hugs and kisses, Anne-So!
Maybe one day we'll find
the body of Anne-Sophie Girard!