A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
Good evening!
And welcome
to a new McFly and Carlito video.
- What are we gonna talk about tonight?
- Bats... and scary stories.
It's on. The first story
is that of Marie-Jacqueline.
- Marie-Jacqueline.
- Marie-Jacqueline!
Motherfucker!
Three comedians.
Can you twerk with your back?
A haunted place.
What is that, guys?
Paranormal missions.
Do you regret murdering a human being?
Traps.
I love you,
but I'll punch you if you sneak up on me.
Challenges.
I'm alive in a fucking tomb!
For the most scared...
- There are noises, bro!
- What?
...a punishment!
Right now, I just want...
to go back home.
A game that's going to last...
...until dawn.
SOMEWHERE IN NORTHERN FRANCE...
We don't know where we are,
and that's a bit scary.
The situation is already scary.
See?
Why did I say yes?
Holy cow! Look, there's a gate there.
- There's an envelope!
- Did you hear that?
What's that? Fuck!
He grabbed my dick!
- I want to go home!
- He actually grabbed my dick!
- I've never seen anything like that.
- No, guys...
He got scared and squeezed my dick.
Who does that?
Can you hold this? I'll read this.
"Careful, beyond this gate,
you'll be inside Château d'Esquelbecq,
the White Lady's domain." No.
Yes. The White Lady.
And we're not talking about the cocktail,
but the legend,
with the scary castle, moats,
and drawbridge.
"In the 17th century, a violent murder
took place, followed by a sordid hanging.
Ever since, a white lady
has haunted the castle
and strange occurrences are reported."
Okay, hold on. The White Lady, guys?
I'm gonna freak the fuck out.
If we're scared,
are we allowed to pull on dicks?
MIDNIGHT - SIX HOURS BEFORE DAWN
Let's go, delinquents.
- This gate squeaks.
- Listen to the sound.
Damn, that's creepy as shit.
Exactly, my man. The goal of the game
is to face your fears.
I'm definitely
the weakest link of the trio,
because when I'm scared, I freeze.
And to avoid the punishment
for the biggest chicken,
you have to play with the others' fears.
Fuck!
- No, really?
- It's already started, actually.
So, this isn't really scary. It's stupid.
I would say McFly
is gonna take defeat in the face.
Natoo or McFly, but surely not me.
Hold on. Listen.
Don't make a sound and listen.
Holy shit!
They're fucking geese!
You know what? Let's go. No questions.
No, we're asking a ton of questions!
The answers to all their questions
must be found in this 13th-century castle.
A thousand square meters of creepy stuff
sitting on five hectares
of even creepier stuff.
So you won't miss
any of this dreadful night,
cameras placed
from the basement to the attic
are going to record all the weird stuff
that will happen. Okay, Carlito?
Carlito?
Hey! What?
- Idiot. What did you say?
- Your name.
What?
He didn't have anything to say.
- Careful. I'm turning this thing on.
- I don't want you to.
Hello?
Hello and welcome to the headquarters.
Here you'll find all the equipment
for tonight's paranormal missions.
Brass rods,
presence detectors,
a pendulum, even some chairs
for those who freak out.
Okay, let's sit down, friends,
because right now I'm about to faint.
This is the first note.
It starts with my name. Fuck!
"McFly,
on January 21, 1655,
the owner of this place,
Marie-Jacqueline Trieste,
was taking her bath.
A disagreement erupted
and her servant smashed her head
against the bathtub.
In order to question the owner's ghost,
you'll relive the conditions
of her murder in that bathtub."
First mission: a midnight bath for McFly,
with Natoo and Carlito
in front of the monitors.
Three, two, one...
- Everything just turned on!
- Damn!
- "Castle of the White Lady."
- You have to go to the second floor.
- No, I can't do this.
- Yes.
- Do you see yourself going alone?
- No.
Not at all.
MISSION ONE
THE BLOODY BATHTUB
Once I'm at the top of the stairs,
where's the bathroom?
- It should be left and left.
- Left.
Fuck, what do I have to do?
Open the doors?
Motherfucker!
Fuck, guys, it's horrible!
- There's nothing.
No, there's not nothing at all.
This is horrible!
What is this, guys?
There's a bathtub that smells like death.
Is that blood?
Strip down to your underwear.
No.
Yeah, I got it.
I'm going to relive this shit.
Bingo!
No. Come on. No.
Well, yes. According to ghost hunters,
putting yourself in the situation
can provoke the victim's spirit
from beyond.
So, McFly... swim trunks on.
That body!
That's her, the White Lady.
Guys, I'm fucking shaking. It's horrible.
No. Fuck no.
You're supposed to call
the ghost of Marie-Jacqueline.
"Cover your eyes
to enhance your other senses
and sound propagates easier in liquid."
So, now submerge yourself up to your ears.
In the water, blindfolded,
ears submerged,
McFly will hear all the noises
in the room perfectly,
including those
from Marie-Jacqueline's spirit...
if it appears.
It's cold!
That cold?
Fuck! That's horrible.
My lower abdomen.
What the fuck am I doing?
- Fuck! That breaks my heart.
- It's awful.
It's awful.
Everything's okay. That face.
- I love you so much, sweetheart.
- We love you so much.
- What should I do?
- You're gonna ask her questions.
For example: did the servant
have reasons to dislike you?
Was she jealous?
- I can't. Fuck!
- It's awful. I never would've done that.
Did your servant
have reasons to dislike you?
Guys, I feel stuff. I swear.
Okay...
It's not physical stuff.
It's just stuff I'm feeling.
Okay.
Things I'm feeling.
It's horrible being in the water.
Fuck, that's horrible.
Is she really the one
who murdered you?
Fucking motherfucker!
Guys, I'm getting out of this bathtub.
There was something, noises.
It's horrible.
I don't know how to explain it.
Like something in the bathtub was moving.
You handled that so well.
That's hell on Earth.
Motherfucker...
It was horrible for me to wait so long.
Holy shit!
Something happened in the tub?
FOUR HOURS AND 45 MINUTES BEFORE DAWN
There was stuff in the water.
I'm gonna try to start from the beginning.
There was a noise in the bathtub.
Horrible!
I'm so happy that's over.
Between Marie-Jacqueline's spirit
and Lady Carlito,
McFly is on track
for the biggest chicken's punishment.
But the night is far from over.
"The villagers say
the White Lady would haunt the gardens...
in search of a tomb,
which she was never given.
Carlito, to free her soul,
you will be buried
with the pendant at HQ,
similar to the one she had.
With the pendant in hand,
call Marie-Jacqueline's ghost."
Me, outside, buried, calling the ghost?
"The movement detector
that McFly will put on the tomb
will confirm her passage underground.
Carlito, take the pendant
and the oxygen tank."
- That's the scariest sentence.
- Go on. Test it.
Put your mouth on it. And you breathe.
Now, in terms of creepy...
MISSION TWO
THE TOMB
...it can't get worse.
In this forest, Marie-Jacqueline
was buried by her murderer
before her body was uncovered by a dog.
Yeah, a mutt.
So, a pretty dark story.
I see a cross.
- What? A cross?
- No!
- Holy shit.
- That's atrocious.
So now, the idea is
to ask Marie-Jacquie's spirit
to come rest in a four-star grave.
Okay, two stars.
- What's that insect?
- A spider. Wait. I'll get it out.
Yeah, I'll get it.
I'm anxious just seeing you in there.
- I just realized what I'm about to do.
- Don't think about it.
- That's your mistake.
- My God. Guys!
- Bro.
- It's atrocious.
This is the worst thing in the world.
Sorry, I dropped some dirt...
Fuck!
- Come on. Close the lid.
- Bro, you're a king.
Fuck! Plus, it's tight in here.
- Yeah?
- It's horrible.
Holy shit, doing this
is unbelievable. Fuck.
I'm gonna set up
the movement detector, okay?
Man, if anything goes wrong,
you handle it, all right?
Yeah, don't worry.
The movement detector.
It's very simple.
It's like a house alarm, but for ghosts.
If someone comes near,
it's gonna make noises and flash.
The movement detector is in place, bro.
- I'm leaving. Later. I love you.
- I'm alive in a fucking tomb!
Marie-Jacqueline. If you're there,
Marie-Jacqueline, show yourself.
We need to understand...
that you're there.
I heard a noise.
- What did you hear?
- What noise?
A fucking noise!
There's nothing on the monitor.
Fuck, it's horrible.
Marie-Jacqueline, please,
if you're there,
make some noise.
Marie-Jacqueline, are you there?
There's noise, bro!
What's going on, bro? Come back!
Fuck! This is horrible!
I'm out of here. I don't give a shit!
I'm leaving the oxygen tank.
Come on. Let's go get him.
Fuck, this is horrible!
I don't know where I am!
- Bro!
- I see you.
- Bro.
- Are you okay?
Fuck, I heard noises.
I thought you felt something
in the tomb.
No!
There's noise over there.
Bro, come quick!
Okay.
What craziness.
Holy shit, seeing you
locked in that tomb...
It's crazy stressful.
Would you have done it?
- It's crazy.
- Fuck.
At this point, Carlito and McFly
have already freaked out.
I'm out of here! I don't give a shit!
But Carlito also made McFly freak out.
So at the moment,
the biggest chicken is McFly.
Unless he's got something up his sleeve,
like... I don't know... Hide and Clap.
I suggest we play Hide and Clap.
When you say clap, I'll go...
- No.
- It gives you a clue about where I am.
Are you guys game?
Yeah.
Let's go. I'm gonna hide.
Later. I'm gonna go see
the White Lady alone.
I think he must've gone upstairs.
Three, two, one...
- Clap!
It's close.
Yeah, but I don't dare go in.
Motherfucker!
Ready for another?
Three, two, one...
- Clap!
- Fuck, it's getting further.
- He's further. He's moving.
- You're not allowed to move!
- Mobile Hide and Seek is cheating.
I love you,
but I'll punch you if you sneak up on me.
You have the same reflex.
Fuck!
- If there were... What?
- Go on!
- Let's go. Back to back.
- Go on.
Go on. Push me!
- I hate going backwards.
- There are a lot of bats. Really a lot.
- Okay, three, two, one, clap!
He's really close. That's why.
I'm sure.
- Or in a big box.
- I don't know.
- He's gonna scare you for no reason.
- Careful or you're gonna get punched, bro!
- He's in an armchair.
- He's here. Three, two, one, clap!
I made you freak out!
Fuck, let's hide.
No! I don't have a flashlight.
It's not fair.
I don't have a flashlight, guys.
Fuck!
Now watch what it's like
not to bat an eye.
You're gonna see a man
who's not afraid.
Are you ready?
Hello!
- "Gonna see a man who's not afraid."
- You're not scared.
You're crazy.
I'm the least scared guy of all time.
I screamed at the top of my lungs,
and you jumped a little.
But he said, "Hello,"
and I fell to the ground.
Nice try, but McFly
got caught in his own game.
Now, if he doesn't want the punishment,
he has to find something
during Natoo's mission...
TWO HOURS AND 53 MINUTES BEFORE DAWN
...with the murderer's spirit.
"In order to conceal her crime,
the servant waited until night
to drag her master's body
out of the bathroom and hide it.
Quickly suspected,
the servant was chained up in the cellar
as she awaited her final punishment:
death by hanging."
Fuck.
"Since then, her ghost
has often appeared in the cellar.
Natoo...
go downstairs
and look for the servant's ghost
to ask her why she did what she did.
- Take the divining rods."
- That's not cool at all.
I don't know how to use them.
Okay, quick tutorial.
Step one: Hold the rods in your hands.
Step two: Ask the ghost questions.
Step three: If the answer is yes,
the rods spread apart.
If the answer is no, they cross.
Simple. Basic.
Is my name really Nathalie, aka Natoo?
- There you go.
- The dowser is speaking!
- Good.
- Okay.
MISSION THREE
THE SERVANT'S CELLAR
Do you see me?
Go on.
Yeah, we see you.
There, we see you again.
It's really funny.
- Those leggings are crazy.
- Guys.
You can see me, then?
- Yes.
- We see you.
- Look, there's a little camera.
- To be sure, what am I doing?
- She's twerking.
- She's twerking her back.
She's really twerking.
Can you twerk with your back?
Twerk with my back? Okay.
That's majestic.
You need to keep going.
If there's someone in the back,
I won't hesitate to knock you out.
I'm so scared, I'm gonna puke.
Honestly, I have nothing
to do with this mess.
I have nothing to do with this.
- Guys!
- What?
I hear footsteps. I hate this part.
"First thing: recreate the moment's energy
by sitting on the edge of the bed
like the servant."
Fuck...
The thing is...
if something happens to me,
I'm deep in a cellar. Really.
"Here is the next mission.
Turn off all the lights."
I can't!
- I know. It's the hardest thing.
- Being in the dark scares me the most.
- You're doing fine.
- We love you.
I swear... Once, I spent an entire night,
six hours straight, frozen in the dark
because I heard some noises.
I admit it's crazy,
but listen, we see everything
and nothing's there.
Nothing.
You're alone.
You can relax, completely alone.
The first question to ask,
"Was your master mean to you?"
I'm letting you contact her.
We're here. We're not leaving.
Was your master mean to you?
Asshole...
They're spreading a little.
That means yes.
I think they're spreading. I'm not well.
- I'm gonna curl up in fear.
- Do you trust me or not?
Do you trust me or not?
Put this on.
Are you nice?
Will you be nice to me?
You won't hurt me?
Was your act premeditated?
Yes?
Yeah? Okay.
We all make mistakes.
Maybe you regret your actions?
Do you regret murdering a human being?
I really didn't move the rods...
and they said, "No."
I'm not okay...
Can I leave?
I'll put it on backwards.
I'm such an idiot.
- We can see your face.
- Yeah.
I hear whispering!
What's that?
Servant?
Boys?
I failed.
Wait.
I saw his big white sneakers sticking out.
Yeah... It's about time
the sun started rising.
So who will be chosen for the punishment?
In my opinion, it's McFly.
No, Carlito.
Or maybe Natoo.
"Friends, it's time to choose
who the biggest chicken was."
It's vexing. I have to say.
Let's agree on the punishment.
This scariest thing...
for the biggest chicken
is the tomb.
Yeah, the tomb.
Seriously, guys?
Why would I go in the tomb?
For what reason?
'Cause you were the least brave, clearly.
Sorry.
You guys are assholes.
That's a horrible thing to do.
THE PUNISHMENT
I'm gonna show you
I'm not the biggest chicken.
- Can you close it?
- Come on. Let's go.
I hope...
I don't fart in my tomb. Can you imagine?
Hey, guys? What's that noise?
McFly, you have more subscribers
than me on Instagram, right?
- Yeah, but...
- Do you think that pisses me off?
- It's because I post regularly.
- Don't worry.
Stop, please! I didn't do that to you!
I just farted.