A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
Jean, I'm nice
Jean, are you there?
Jean, did you get rid of the demon?
Hold on a second!
Fuck! Son of a--
Three comedians.
This reminds me of when I worked
at an S&M club.
A haunted place.
The detector detected some stuff. Fuck!
Son of a--
Paranormal missions.
- What's that?
- There was something.
Traps.
I'm gonna make them crack.
Fuck!
Challenges.
- Can you?
- No, I can't.
- I can.
- What?
For the most scared...
a punishment!
No, I can't!
The game will last...
until dawn.
SOMEWHERE IN CHARENTE-MARITIME...
- Friends!
- This is crazy.
This is crazy.
I'm unfazed.
I'm actually scared.
I'm really, really, really too scared.
Everything's gonna be fine.
The ghosts are friendly.
The ghosts are nice.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
- This is heavy, like...
- What?
- That's what it is? There's a paper.
- Can I open it?
"Welcome to this abandoned
18th-century hospital."
A hospital!
For starters, it's already worrisome,
but it's been abandoned since the '80s?
A nightmare!
Eighty thousand square meters
eroded by sickness and ghosts.
Okay, that's it. I don't feel well.
"Numerous patients died as a result
of cholera, the plague, and rabies.
They say this place is haunted.
You'll spend the night here
to investigate the presence of ghosts."
Fuck!
Am I the one who's gonna be haunted?
Damn!
I'm not scared.
It's just a hospital. There.
Not scared?
We'll see, my friend...
since the goal of tonight's game
is actually to face your fears...
- Why did I say yes?
- I don't know why we said yes.
...and to play with the others' fears.
- Fuck, you're an idiot!
- Asshole.
You're such an idiot! Fuck, no!
Idiot, I don't know,
but, in any case,
Noom has understood the idea.
At dawn, they will decide
who was the most scared,
and that person will endure a punishment.
Let the game begin!
- Go in.
- Go on, Djimo.
MIDNIGHT - SIX HOURS BEFORE DAWN
- Fuck!
- What? Walkers? Why the fuck?
- What was that?
- It's the wind!
- What?
- Calm down, guys.
- The wind.
Left or right?
Four levels of never-ending hallways
and run-down rooms.
On the second floor, a headquarters.
Equipment, control monitors,
surveillance cameras...
Considering how wrecked the building is,
we're lucky to still have electricity.
There you go. As if by chance!
Okay.
Look there. There's something there.
"Restart the current
to activate the surveillance monitors.
Find the transformer box in the basement."
Why the basement, bro? Stop!
Find the box...
"The cellars are dangerous.
You risk bothering the bats
with noise and light.
Noom should go alone."
No!
Like in horror films,
the black guy always dies first.
That stinks, like ammonia.
Hold on. What's this?
Fucking rats! Do they want to kill me?
Fuck!
Fuck, I can't!
Fuck, it's huge! I want to die!
Fuck, rats!
I can't. Rats, fuck!
Rats!
Why didn't Djimo come here?
Rats! There are rats!
I can't!
They're so big, you might say rabbits.
Focus!
Okay.
It's not working.
Fuck! I'm hot.
Noom sees two little mice,
and he's already about to die.
- Are you okay, Noom?
- Look at how hot I am. I'm sweating.
Rats!
All right. To determine
who's to be the most scared tonight,
we'll start the paranormal missions.
First folder.
"In the 19th century,
this hospital welcomed Jean Brassau,
a patient said to have been
possessed by the devil.
He died within the hospital walls
with a crucifix in hand
after several weeks of isolation.
- He will maybe respond via music."
- Via music? That sounds like shit.
No! It's well known
that music has virtues
for clearing energy.
It's practical to exorcise rooms.
So the possessed spirit of Jean
should show itself with sketchy noises
thanks to an old ukulele piece,
played by the musician of the group, Lola.
Jean, you're so nice
I want to meet you
We'll go for pizza
- It's time to go, Lola.
- I'm not well.
MISSION ONE
JEAN THE POSSESSED
Djimo?
- Yes?
- Walkie-talkie to say to go right.
- You should go right.
Control monitor to see Lola.
We see you. Go forward a little.
Noom and Djimo
can watch everything from HQ.
I'm freaking out all alone.
No, I'm not feeling well at all!
What would really scare me
would be seeing a ghost,
something that surprised me.
That could make me leave.
She's completely fucked.
We're gonna do everything so she fucks up.
No, I'm not going.
I swear, one of you has to come.
There's nothing. I swear. We can see.
- There's nothing at all.
- No! Fuck!
- I swear, this isn't funny.
- We see it all.
But there's nothing! There's a chair...
Jean, I'm nice
Jean, I'm friendly
Jean, are you there?
Jean, you're nice
I don't doubt it
I have something in my bag.
We can freak her out.
Let's do it.
- There's nothing, guys.
- Let's tell her to come back.
- We can freak her out on the way back.
- Okay.
We came up with a plan to freak Lola out.
We're dressing up as ghosts.
She's gonna freak out!
Let's hope so!
Because the costume budget was big.
With such means, we can be sure
that something crazy will happen to Lola,
but it won't be on account of them.
Jean, can you tell me if you're there?
Jean, can you tell me if you're here?
No!
Holy fuck!
Holy fuck. Something fell!
I'm coming back. I'm out of here!
I'm leaving!
Fuck!
Fucking shit!
Guys!
I was too freaked out.
I'm sure he was there.
I'm totally sure.
I'm... Guys?
Really, you're total assholes.
Enter Jean's ghost...
Holy shit!
And the ghosts of Noom and Djimo.
Lola gets closer to the punishment
destined for the most scared.
But come on! You can't give up
and you have overcome your fears...
FOUR HOURS AND 30 MINUTES BEFORE DAWN
...in this creepy hospital.
"Some of the sick who were possessed
or had psychiatric issues
were attached to pillars in the solarium
at times when their soul
could be purified by the sun.
Can you attach yourself
to one of the pillars?
I can't.
- I say I can't.
- I can't at all. I can really feel souls.
I can.
- What?
Apparently, Djimo wants to prove
the most scared tonight will not be him.
In any case, for Lola,
this is the perfect chance
to get her revenge.
They're sending me to take a little nap.
You're not there to sleep.
You're there to suffer.
This reminds me of when I worked
at an S&M club.
- We're covering your eyes now.
- You're insane. No!
- You wanted to be the man, bro.
- No.
You said you could do it.
- Fuck.
- Don't worry.
Bro, it's nothing.
- There?
- We're gonna attach you there.
Where are you gonna attach me now?
- Don't worry.
- Your ordeal has only just begun.
Guys!
I'm gonna get back at Djimo
for the ghosts.
- I'm listening.
- I'm not telling you. You'll see.
That's enough, guys!
Who's there?
What's that?
Son of a bitch! Asshole! Go!
Rats! Fucking jerks!
Not a rat!
Get it off me!
I really got you, bro.
Well done!
Djimo!
What?
Are you okay?
No!
- I'm coming.
- Fuck, what's that?
- I can't help you, bro.
- Son of a bitch!
Fuck, there are rats!
- Fucking shit!
- Wait!
Careful! They're gonna devour your balls.
They're gonna devour your balls. Wait!
Lola! She's not scared of rats.
Lola!
Fuck, it's huge!
You're not brave men.
- I don't like rats at all.
- You're chickens!
Come on, HQ, friends.
HQ!
I'm super happy with my prank!
Well done, Lola.
TWO HOURS AND 45 MINUTES BEFORE DAWN
While getting back at Djimo,
she also freaked Noom out.
But let's get back to work. Tonight's
second paranormal mission is on.
"A few years ago, on the ground floor,
the surgery area
was completely burned down.
In this toxic universe,
ghosts are always present.
They show themselves
through different forms of heat.
Thanks to this thermal camera,
you're going to verify
if any souls still live there.
The chosen ones:
Noom and Lola."
- Fuck!
- Don't--
- I won't scare you.
- No, no pranks.
I raise my hand. No pranks.
Friendship is beautiful.
No pranks.
Well, anyway, let's go.
Let's put on our pretty little outfits.
Careful of the debris
in the burned zone on the ground floor.
Great, guys. Let's go.
I'm counting on you.
Go ahead. Count on us, bro.
MISSION TWO
BURNED ZONE
Djimo, where do we go?
- You're sure it was there?
- Right.
Look, hard hat required.
- Not another heat source.
- It stinks.
Lola and Noom go off
in search of the heat source.
And we won't mention the radiator,
just a ghost consumed
by the flames of Hell.
Just saying that freaks me out.
Put the camera in front.
- Put the camera in front.
- Something just passed by.
Put the camera in front.
What is is?
Can you hear me?
Are you okay, Djimo?
Djimo?
- Man, let's go back up.
- No, we have to explore the room.
Today, they're gonna get
the scare of the their lives.
I'm gonna kill them.
Let's go back to back.
I'll watch the rear, you watch the front.
It was really burned here.
When you look at the wall like this,
there's nothing...
- What?
- I swear there was a noise!
- I made a noise.
- No.
- It was me. I knocked on the door.
- No, there.
- There was a sound.
- Wait. Don't move.
Look with the thermal camera, please.
What was that?
There's a heat presence there.
I admit there was something.
- Wait. What's that?
- It smells like fire, man.
I'm gonna make them crack.
Hold on. Slowly.
- There's smoke! Let's get out of here!
- What's that?
Stop screaming! You're scaring me!
Hold on.
Fuck! Son of a bitch!
Asshole!
I knew you were gonna... I knew it!
I was stuck on the smell of fire.
- So, what did you see?
- First, we have to take a break.
We saw three dots on the wall.
- I'm not well.
- What did you see?
There were three dots on the wall.
I so feel like leaving.
Since you didn't respond,
I thought you'd come freak us out.
From that point on, I was focused on you
and I was ready for anything.
I'm not well.
At the moment, Lola and Djimo
have played their best pranks.
Noom awaits his turn.
But there's not much time since
there's only one mission left before dawn.
ONE HOUR AND 30 MINUTES BEFORE DAWN
"In the 1960s, a young boy named Léon
lived in the hospital's apartment
with his parents for nearly 12 years.
Since then, the young boy's voice
has been heard multiple times
by a succession
of hospital security guards.
Goal of the mission:
go to that apartment to play
'Red Light, Green Light' with Léon.
Don't forget your bag
with the presence detectors."
This high-tech device captures
variations in the electromagnetic field.
When a ghost is in the vicinity,
it will beep and flash.
It's a little like at an auto shop,
but I assure you it works.
"The chosen one: Djimo!
Note: The key to the apartment included."
You took my finger, man!
Look. He doesn't feel like going.
MISSION THREE
LÉON'S ROOM
Fucking motherfucker.
What is this fucking room?
Can you hear me?
We hear you really bad.
Do you hear us?
It's okay. I hear you.
I'll explain to you quickly.
You have to set up
and turn on the three detectors
in a line behind you
so you can see if he gets closer
during the game.
- What?
- Asshole.
Fuck!
You have to find a wall to play the game
and set up the presence detectors
in three different spots
in a line behind you.
If little Léon's spirit is there,
they're gonna detect it.
But since it's a very sensitive device,
Djimo needs to place them very delicately.
Djimo, you have to turn off
the walkie-talkie, face the wall,
and ask Léon to play with you.
Fuck.
Okay.
Do you want to play
"Red Light, Green Light" with me?
Red light!
The detector.
Hold on!
- What's that?
- I turned that toy off.
Stop with your
"I turned that toy off" shit. Wait!
It's starting to get crazy.
The detector detected some stuff. Fuck.
That asshole is here.
It's super nerve-wracking.
I'm gonna try.
- Do you want to go?
- Djimo, come back.
We're gonna switch.
That's crazy.
The room is already scary as hell,
and the boy was there.
The boy was there.
Noom, didn't you want to go?
- It's my turn to go.
- You want to go do it?
Noom is a little too motivated.
Doesn't it smell like a prank?
Seeing as he went to the basement
to turn on the lights,
he also knows how to turn them off.
Fuck, the lights went out!
They all went out! Fuck!
Noom! Please! Fuck!
- Fuck! What's going on?
- It's too weird.
- I'm gonna go.
- I'm coming with you.
Look behind. I'll look ahead.
Noom.
Fuck! Why are we here?
Noom, fuck. Respond.
Noom.
He's gonna be in the closet.
Did you see him before?
Son of a bitch!
I hate you! Fuck! Die!
THIRTY MINUTES BEFORE DAWN
You're such an asshole.
That's what I was saying.
You're both total assholes.
The goal was to make you freak out.
There you go.
- If I can scare people...
- Mission accomplished.
Thanks.
After that last stunt from Noom,
the sun is rising
over the old abandoned hospital.
It's time for Lola, Noom, and Djimo
to decide...
Who was the biggest chicken tonight?
We have to vote. I propose everyone say
who was the biggest chicken on three.
- Okay.
- One...
two...
three.
- Djimo!
- Lola!
That's true.
You freaked out.
- The biggest chicken?
- Yeah, you.
Did you see his face in the room?
His eyes?
He was freaking out so much,
they were blue.
- On the bed with the rats.
- He was not okay.
You both said Djimo?
- We both did say Djimo.
- There you go, in any case.
THE PUNISHMENT
- See you!
- See you never!
Big kiss.
Don't leave me here.
Kisses for the ghosts
- Bye.
- Don't leave me here! Fuck!
- Goodbye, hospital!
- Let's go. It's time.
Motherfuckers, come and untie me!
Bye, Djimo!
Fuck!
Come and untie me!