A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
Fuck.
Three comedians.
- You don't find your faces scary?
- I don't.
A haunted place.
Paranormal missions.
It's too much. Way too much!
Traps.
Issa!
Challenges.
In there?
For the most scared...
Damn!
...a punishment!
Salaam alaikum, Mr. Ghost!
A game that's going to last...
until dawn.
SOMEWHERE IN DORDOGNE...
Here we go!
We're in the middle of a forest
with a lake in front of us.
It's scary.
- Fadily?
- Yeah?
What would freak you out the most?
Honestly, what would freak me out...
would be hearing some noise,
- like footsteps coming toward us.
- Damn!
I don't dare look ahead!
Damn! This is scary as hell.
You're damn right it is.
This is Château-l'Évêque
and its abandoned village.
A place form the 14th century,
so dark that even moonbeams
struggle to shine through.
And the aim of tonight's game
is to face your fears...
- Did you hear that weird noise?
- No, I didn't.
...and to play with other people's fears.
- Issa is already preparing pranks...
- I'm waiting for the girls.
I'll try to scare them.
...because at dawn, they'll decide
who was the biggest chicken
and punish him or her.
- It's horrible.
- Horrible.
- Wait! You're going too fast!
- Stay with me. Bugs are everywhere.
- It's disgusting.
- I'm panicking.
Fadily, stay with me!
Don't look back.
You know what? We're okay.
Son of a bitch! An owl!
A freaking owl!
There's an owl in front of us,
blocking our way!
Wait, I hear...
I hear the girls already.
They're screaming. This is crazy.
On three, we walk like it's nothing.
One, two, three, let's go.
Fuck!
- Look. They're backing up in a weird way.
- They're gonna fly away.
Did you see how big their wings are?
We're just trying to pass by.
You do what you need to do.
Okay, damn. You've got some balls.
Okay, Hedwige, what do you say now?
My God! I was so scared.
So now we've managed
to get out of the forest.
Issa?
I think it's... It's the truck.
It's the headquarters! Fuck yeah.
Fuck! He's getting on my nerves!
- Did you have a good trip?
- He's so childish.
- How's it going, girls?
- We're good.
- Yeah.
- Issa?
Hey, Issa. We came face-to-face
with two owls.
How are they doing?
- You don't know how freaked out we were!
- No, you don't. We were sweating!
Let's get in the truck.
It's the scariest thing I've done.
This Scooby-Doo van
parked at the castle gates
will serve as their headquarters,
with equipment for the paranormal
missions, such as monitoring screens,
surveillance cameras...
and even a little note card
to understand the history
of this huge 900-square-meter castle.
Fadily, let's go.
"A bishop savagely murdered...
deadly illnesses,
owners who hastily ran away
from the place...
Which of you will be the most scared?"
If you want to go look around,
I can tell you where to go... from afar.
To be honest, since I saw the owls,
I wouldn't bet on myself.
Just now, I feel Laurie's hand on my arm.
It's cutting off the blood flow!
Friendship is a beautiful thing.
But they won't stay friends too long,
because it's time
for the first paranormal mission.
"In 1575, Monseigneur Fournier,
Bishop of Périgueux and its village,
was savagely strangled by his servants
who wanted to steal his treasure.
Ever since, his ghost
has been haunting the place.
His heart still beats inside the rocks
of the stairs where he was murdered.
Laurie, you're going to meet
with this ghost
and try to hear his heartbeat."
Come on.
Wait, help me out, guys.
I'm going out on a mission all by myself.
Don't worry. We have walkie-talkies.
Sis, you're here, and you have to go...
Wait. Where are the bishop's stairs?
All the way over there!
- On the second floor.
- What?
Man, are you crazy?
MISSION 1
THE BISHOP'S STAIRS
Laurie, "Trapped by his servants,
the bishop was savagely strangled
on the 50th step of the stairs."
- We can count together if you want.
- No, it's okay.
Count correctly.
Wait. One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven...
eight, nine, ten,
11, 12,
13, 14, 15, 16,
17, 18, 19, 20, 21...
22...
23...
24...
I hear noises.
What do you hear?
It's like a door slamming, you know?
A door that wasn't closed properly.
Yeah, but girl, it's windy in there.
45...
46...
47...
48...
49...
And... 50!
Now she must get the stethoscope out
to try and hear the weird noises
of these cursed stairs.
Lights off.
Monseigneur Fournier...
if you're here...
reveal yourself with a noise I can hear
with the stethoscope.
What's happening?
So there was a noise,
like something opened...
It's not scary when it's quiet,
but as soon as something happens, man,
it feels like my insides drop.
Monseigneur Fournier,
my name is Laurie Peret.
Please don't freak me out.
Be right back.
I'm going to the foot of the tower.
For real, I hear...
noises like cracking...
Monseigneur Fournier, are you there?
I can't get out! It's closed!
Issa!
- Issa!
- Yes, Laurie?
- Open this motherfucking door!
- Hold on.
- Fuck.
- What's going on?
What's up? You're shaking.
THREE HOURS AND 30 MINUTES BEFORE DAWN
Issa outdid himself with that.
He slammed the door so discreetly
that he managed to pass as the hero.
- Let me tell you what happened.
- Yeah, tell us.
Upstairs, I could feel a presence,
you know?
I think maybe someone was there.
I ran down the stairs
and the door slammed right in front of me,
and it was impossible to open.
- There was nothing on the cameras.
- You know what happened?
It was you, asshole!
Issa!
Tonight, I'm not sure
what will be worse for the girls:
hunting ghosts or staying with Issa.
- Fadily?
- Yeah?
"In the 16th century,
the village women
who worked as servants in the castle
all died suddenly
because of a terrible fever.
This fever would appear
after the women came back from the attic
where they hung the laundry.
Fadily, it's your turn to go upstairs
to contact the washerwomen's ghosts
and find out
what caused these strange deaths."
- In the attic.
- Let's start with that, bro.
I have to take the bishop's stairs.
Then go to an attic.
I have to talk to people.
Plus, they say those
who come down get a fever?
This is crazy.
Well, what's really crazy
is knowing all that and still thinking,
"I'm going in, guys."
MISSION 2
THE WASHERWOMEN
- Okay, guys. I'm going in.
- Fadily, I'm right here with you.
Come on. Let's go upstairs.
Don't think about it. Just go.
I was acting all tough downstairs,
but I'm scared as hell.
I have to keep going up? Hold on.
- Damn!
- What did you find?
I don't know.
I thought I saw something move.
- No.
- Go on inside. Turn on the lights.
No, why the hell am I here?
Get the pendulum...
to make contact with the ghosts.
Good luck.
Don't worry. You got this.
Okay.
Okay, servants and washerwomen...
If you're here,
make the pendulum move to my right.
Wait.
She's scared.
Hold on. I need to breathe right now.
I swear I'm not making this up.
It moved a little bit.
Okay, are you there?
If you are, move to the right.
She's shaking so much, it's crazy.
Yeah.
I feel like crying.
Was the fever the cause of your death?
If so, move the pendulum to the right.
If not, to the left.
Damn.
I heard somebody say something!
I'm getting out of here!
I'm done with this! Stop!
I heard somebody say something!
I'm done. I heard somebody talking.
Fuck.
Stop it! Fuck! Don't talk to me.
I'm getting out of here. I'm done. Stop.
I'm done for real.
TWO HOURS AND 15 MINUTES BEFORE DAWN
- What happened upstairs?
- I swear, at some point, I heard...
someone about to speak,
but I didn't let it happen. I left.
Damn, I can't do this.
- So you think there was someone upstairs?
- I don't know.
- The pendulum was moving for real?
- It was!
As for the competition,
Fadily did exactly like Laurie
and freaked the hell out.
Except this time,
Issa had nothing to do with it.
When I told you that this castle was
haunted and no one believed me...
Well, there you go.
I think I'm the biggest chicken.
I don't know about that.
I left at the end. I couldn't take it.
I think I'm telling on myself right now.
For the punishment,
it's basically between the girls.
It's now Issa's turn
to show how brave he is
with tonight's third paranormal mission,
linked to a rather enjoyable legend...
"A few years ago, some new owners
attempted to buy the abandoned castle
to turn it into a hotel.
However, just a few weeks later,
they ran away abruptly
without even taking their belongings.
Since then, strange events
have been occurring in that room.
People have heard noises,
and the boxes never stay
in the same place.
Issa, try to make contact
with the ghosts that occupy this room
- to understand why they prevented..."
- You think it's funny?
"...the new owners from moving in
and attack those who enter the castle."
Fuck.
Let's go.
I really hope you shit yourself,
you asshole.
And I'm gonna come close
the door behind you.
If things get out of control,
scream and I swear I'll come running.
What can he scream to...
- Shareh!
- Say it again.
It means you're dead.
- Let's go, Issa. Good luck.
- Shareh!
- Shareh.
- You didn't come.
Can you hear me?
Okay, let's go.
MISSION 3
THE ROOM FULL OF BOXES
Salaam alaikum, Mr. Ghost.
I don't give a fuck! You can scare me.
I believe in God!
ONE HOUR AND 35 MINUTES BEFORE DAWN
- There's a tower right there on my right.
- That's the one.
- Hello?
- Yeah?
I see the stairs.
Well, take the stairs.
It should be on the fourth floor.
Did you enter a room?
- Girls?
- Yeah?
Wallah, I hear sounds.
Subhan Allah wallah, on the Quran,
I hear noises.
- Really?
- But what's in front of you?
I'm in a room. There's some old furniture,
- an old TV...
- Keep going.
Keep going inside that room?
- Yeah, there are some boxes.
- Are you serious?
Go all the way over there.
- There you go. We see you.
- Go in. It's there.
In there?
In this cursed room
located on the second floor,
Issa must contact the spirit
said to have pushed the occupants
to leave...
What am I supposed to do?
- Put your flashlight and camera down.
- Wait.
Put what down?
I'm not putting anything down.
Get your rods out, Issa.
Hold on, I can hear somebody breathing.
Well, that's not us.
I swear on my life...
- We lost the connection.
- Wait. Shut the fuck up!
What should I do now, girls?
Get your rods out.
This is what you have to do.
You touch them together.
You take them in your hands.
You're gonna ask if there are
any ghosts haunting the room.
Go ahead.
Spirit...
is anyone in this room? If yes...
make the rods cross.
Hey, please. Do you see that or not?
- We really see it.
- This is out of hand. No.
Wallah, I swear to God...
No, this is some crazy shit.
Are you okay?
I have tears in my eyes. This is crazy.
Wait.
He's right to be praying.
Spirit...
show me...
where in this room...
the spirits are.
- What's in front of you?
- There's a box.
- Look in the box.
- What!
- I don't know. Go check it.
- Go look.
- Do you still hear someone breathing?
- I hear breathing.
Breathe, Issa. Breathe.
We're gonna tease him after
like he was making fun of us.
He was gonna cry.
He was making so much fun of us.
He was crying like a baby.
- Sorry. We're making fun of him.
- Look how he's lifting the boxes.
We have no visual. Issa!
- Let go of me!
- Shareh!
Let me go!
- Fucking let go of me!
- Issa?
Let's go. Where is it?
Stay with me, Fadily!
Issa!
FORTY-FIVE MINUTES BEFORE DAWN
It's here.
Issa? We're in the room with boxes.
Issa!
- Issa?
Where is he?
- Hey, don't leave, Fadily.
- Wait.
No.
- Fuck.
- Wait.
What is this childish shit?
There's someone.
Motherfucker!
Honestly, you're so childish.
And with that nice prank by Issa,
the sun rises at the Château-l'Évêque.
Who was the biggest chicken of the night?
Who deserves a punishment?
Who was the most scared?
Who was the least scared?
We should start there.
I think that's Issa.
Okay, Issa freaked out a little bit.
But he mostly
freaked the hell out of the girls.
- Shareh!
- Issa?
So it comes down to Laurie or Fadily.
I'm not gonna lie. I was scared shitless.
You were the biggest chicken.
I admit that I was really scared,
but I wasn't the most scared.
- Okay. Now...
- Deliberation.
We're gonna do what I do when I play
Werewolves of Miller's Hollow.
Everyone, put your finger in the air
like this.
And on three, you point to who you think
was the most scared tonight.
Three, two, one, point.
It's you, sis. Without a doubt.
Okay, so I suggest...
we go back together
and you go back in the van.
- Alone?
- Yeah.
Seriously? Going home in the van?
We expected more from you, Issa.
Well. I guess he still feels guilty
for locking Laurie in.
I swear on my mother's life!
Don't do this to me!
- Or not.
- You're dogs!
- Laurie, we're out.
- Come on.
Please open the door, Fadily.
Don't leave, guys!
Fadily!