Previously on "The Shield".
Hey, Vic, wait a minute. I
just got my job back, okay?
I'm not breaking into this place.
I'm not taking another fall.
You guys go back out there,
I gotta go to Aceveda.
- Let's go.
- You went off the grid today?
- Who told you that?
- Today was a one-time thing. Got it?
- Got it?
- Got it.
On your knees, man.
Let's see that mouth. Suck it!
- She's been crying for you.
- It's been really busy right now.
You're always busy.
That's never stopped you
from coming home before.
These are the serial
numbers of the bills.
They'll get flagged.
We can't spend a nickel until
we know which bills are marked.
Treasury's got Aceveda checking
bills on any bust over a grand.
- List's in Aceveda's safe.
- Well, so that's it.
- Not necessarily.
- It's in a safe...
...in a captain's office,
inside of a police station.
Gotta be a way.
It's freezing out here.
Decoy Squad's in the clubhouse.
We're working late...
...tomorrow night, boys. You
got plans, change them.
I got tickets for Journey.
What's going on?
Getting the list out
of Aceveda's safe.
- What? I thought there was no way.
- All things change.
- The president's in town campaigning.
- In Farmington?
His schedule changed. Added
a stop in Century City.
Takes him right through our
shitty neck of the woods...
...at about 65 miles an hour.
What's that got to do with the list?
Every cop is stuck
on security detail.
Means a skeleton crew in the
Barn all day and night.
You forgetting about the combination?
Aceveda's safe is county-issue.
Means the combination's on file.
Anybody from Property ever
asks you for a favor, do it.
We get one shot. After the
president's gone, that's it.
This works, I might even
have to vote for the guy.
All right.
- I'm going.
- It's 6:00 in the morning.
Come on, you gotta stop that.
It's just one, to start the day.
To go with the other eight butts?
Six of them are yours.
Maybe you should stop too.
All right, that's just
the hormones talking.
My mom knows about the baby.
Jenny opened her big
mouth to my aunt.
Okay, so now she knows.
- God, she's gonna milk this one.
- Come on, she can't be that bad.
Yeah?
I'm the only one that talks to her,
so that means I get all her crap.
Look, don't worry
about your mom, okay?
- You're supposed to be off today.
- Well, now I'm on.
The president's in town.
Bye.
Okay, it's a half an hour before
morning shift is back on duty.
It's a ghost town out there.
Okay.
All right.
Clear. Four, eight, five, two, one.
Shit.
She's here. Nina's here.
Get down, get down.
- Hey, you're here early.
- So are you.
Gotta beat the bad guy to the punch.
Where's the list?
Ask your Property guy when he
pulls his head out of his ass.
Christ.
- Sure you punched in the code right?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
- We gotta figure out another way.
- There is no other way.
Especially when employee of the
month clocks in two hours early.
I might be able to crack the
safe, if I had enough time.
- You ever tried that?
- Never stopped me before.
Look, Shane was in there 30
seconds, we almost got caught.
If we could get the safe
out sometime tonight...
...Ronnie can take his sweet time.
How's Aceveda not gonna
notice a missing safe?
He'll be gone.
Plus, we'll put in a twin.
That safe is standard police-issue.
Gotta be a thousand of them around.
I have to see the detective.
Your girlfriend's back.
Christ. This I don't need right now.
- Detective.
- Mrs. Maldonado.
Reina's friend gave me this song.
It says he killed her. It says
he stabbed and killed mi hija.
This is supposed to be hip?
It sounds like a Chihuahua
threw up on an accordion.
It's a narcocorrido.
A song about crimes.
-Very popular in Mexico.
-Making their way up north.
Chaydez loved her, but
he couldn't have her.
Couldn't let her go.
It's a love song.
Not quite.
As they made love, he stabbed her once
for every day they were together.
And buried her by the underpass
in Frogtown Flats by the river.
- A real chart-topper.
- Who's this victim, Reina?
Fifteen-year-old girl,
disappeared six months ago.
It was Bobby's case. I helped out
for a day checking gang angles.
- And?
- Wasn't gang.
Chaydez worked for her father.
He was the only suspect. I
guess nothing ever came of it.
Ever since Bobby took
early retirement...
...Mom's been coming
to me for updates.
Do we know the singer?
Otilio Ramirez. Self-published. The
cowboy crap is straight ranchero.
Let's see if we can locate him.
Also get a canine unit
and look for the body.
Why?
Because the song says
she's buried there.
We gonna bring in Eminem every
time he raps about killing his ex?
Rap songs are fantasies.
Narcocorridos are recorded history.
Learn something new every day.
If we're looking for a
body, it must be Lauren.
Hey.
Careful. Boris doesn't
play well with other dogs.
I must have the magic touch.
Give him time to know you better.
Heel.
Sit.
So, what brings us
together this time?
Heard a song about a lovesick cholo
buried his chiquita out here.
They brought us out
because of a song?
Look at it as quality time.
-You still got that boyfriend?
-Still got that wife?
No. Still got that boyfriend?
The cook, right?
Chef.
- Find.
- How's that going?
He's trying to establish his career.
Been a while.
Still don't see a ring.
Don't worry, he'll get to it.
Body.
They don't write love
songs like they used to.
Body.
I need more flags.
- Hey, can I get your autograph?
- Yeah, like on a confession.
- Pack up.
- Who are you?
- We're big fans.
- The biggest.
What are you doing?
Let's go.
- He didn't do nothing.
- Yeah?
He seems to know where the
bodies are buried. Don't you?
- You can't silence me.
- No, we're gonna make you talk.
Just get your wiry ass in the car.
- Look, I know all my rights.
- Relax.
- You might get a new album out of it.
-I s that our corridor?
Yeah.
Not as tough as he sings.
They pulled eight bodies out.
All young women in various
stages of decomposition.
Eight?
Well, any of them stabbed?
Some were there too long to tell.
We'll wait for the ME.
So these guys actually write
songs celebrating crimes?
The popular ones get commissioned.
- Musical confessions?
- I'm gonna go see...
...what they recovered from
the dead women's bodies.
- Gonna start with Otilio?
- I'll make him sing.
Your song says that Reina
Maldonado was stabbed to death...
...and dumped by the railroad tracks.
That sound familiar?
My songs speak for themselves.
I'd rather hear it
from you, rock star.
She was 14 years old
when she went missing.
You sing about Chaydez stabbing her.
- What are you doing?
- Trying to find out why your CD...
- ...led us to eight dead women.
- Help!
- Help! You stay away from me.
- Jesus Christ. What's your problem?
- Help!
- What's going on?
Nothing.
- Really.
- I don't wanna be alone with him.
I didn't touch him.
Go look at the tape.
I'll just sit in.
- That's not necessary.
- Everyone's on presidential detail.
I can lend a hand.
Now, where were we?
I don't commit crimes.
I'm a journalist.
Is that what you think you are?
Did Chaydez commission that song?
- A reporter protects his sources.
- Reporters don't protect killers.
I just write the truth.
Arrest me, arrest the L.A. Times too.
Sol Negro needed money
for his family.
Planned to take it from a
liquor store on San Marcos...
...but the shop owner hated Mexicans.
Pulled a gun.
- Sol Negro shot him in the neck.
- I remember that.
- You remember that?
- I sure do, it was Christmas.
Yeah. It can't be this easy, can it?
Otilio's got three CDs. Who knows
how many cases we might close?
Run Sol Negro, see what
street name comes up.
Show the mug shot to the victim.
Who am l, the Strike
Team all of a sudden?
- What?
- That sounded like an order.
It's not.
- How do you wanna go?
- Same way.
It's just, it's nice to be asked.
- Are you arresting Chaydez?
- He's just here for questioning.
- Does he know where Reina is?
- If he knows, I'll know.
Listen, this could take a while.
So why don't you go home...
- ...get a rest?
- I want to stay here.
For the good news.
Hear that, Chaydez?
He's singing about you.
Just a song.
No, it's a map to eight dead girls.
And I got a big bet...
- ...Reina Maldonado is one of them.
- Wrong.
I don't understand why
an asshole like you...
...would put a stabbing to music.
- I didn't write that.
- No.
You killed Reina and had
Otilio write it for you.
- Never happened.
- Narcocorridos are real. Not made up.
The singer's reputation
depends on it.
Now, he sung about a dead body.
We found eight.
You were off my radar,
now you're back.
- Can I see you two outside?
- Later.
Now, I think.
We heard from the lab.
Early best guess says...
...the deaths look like poisoning from
long-term chemical-meth exposure.
Reina hooked up with an
asshole cooking crank?
Maybe not. Her dental
records are on file.
She wasn't there. She wasn't
one of the bodies we pulled.
Maybe there's another burial ground.
So we have a meth operation
that's poisoning its workers...
...and a missing girl.
Claudette, run the meth thing with
Dutch. Vic, you stay with Reina.
- The singer and his muse?
- Keep until we find out more.
How? We're at deadline.
- We got nothing to charge them with.
- Find something.
Secret Service wants to
meet with the captains.
I'll be back in about an hour.
What did he tell me to do?
Drum up charges to hold them?
Trust me, that doesn't work.
He didn't mean it, right?
I could free up part of the
Decoy Squad for a few hours.
Cut Chaydez loose,
keep a tail on him.
- That's your call, not mine.
- I'll take responsibility.
When Walon's team comes
into the Barn, cut him.
Get it inside the clubhouse. Aceveda's
out of the office for an hour.
Decoy Squad's on the way in. Just
enough time to make the switch.
- I really don't like this.
- Well, you'll pretend.
What's with all the Rolaids, man?
- I got an ulcer.
- Since when?
Since the Armenian mob
started looking for me.
- This helps.
- Stop worrying your guts out.
We're not gonna get busted.
Why are we breaking into
a captain's office?
We can nail 20 guys
we lay the cash on...
...get 30 cents on the dollar.
Let them worry about washing it.
Partner up with criminals? Trying
to find the flaw in that plan.
There's other ways...
That are fine if you
want huge risk...
...and 30 cents on the dollar, but
I want a dollar on the dollar.
Hey.
Somebody moving?
Yeah, we're just moving
a little stuff...
...out of the clubhouse. Make
some room for your team.
I thought you wanted us out.
I do. Might as well be all
comfortable in the meantime.
Listen, I heard you guys
came by to help us out.
It beats going home to an empty bed.
I can't help you with that tonight.
Don't worry, I haven't
needed a slumpbuster yet.
Hey, what happened with
the Secret Service?
Got postponed.
Thank you for the help
with the Maldonado case.
I was glad when you
came in when you did.
Listen, I just about wrote
this girl off for dead.
I poked my head into it
for a little while...
...but when we hit the
wall, I just checked out.
- Then make it right.
- You're not hearing me.
Reina's father died a month
ago from a heart attack.
He just couldn't stand his
daughter missing and not knowing.
I was just hoping to get the mom
some good news, that's all.
Well, just keep trying.
- How's your stomach?
- Better when this is done.
- We're halfway home.
- All right.
Let's go.
All right, you're on. You
gotta get inside the safe...
...make a copy of the list
before day shift comes back on.
Glad there's no pressure.
Lend him a Rolaids.
- Three-hole punch?
- Yeah, 3973.
- Tape dispensers?
- I got five units.
Right. Stapler?
Six.
Great, only 57 more to find.
And then we'll see what
our next punishment is.
Look, I told you that I was
gonna go out to Aceveda...
- ...and you still went out there.
- It was the right thing to do.
Maybe, but you could have
also gotten hung out to dry.
It was the right thing.
I had to make a deal with
Aceveda to get my job back.
Tell him if I saw any
cops going out of line.
When I made that promise,
I sure didn't think...
...that you'd be one of them.
One-inch binders?
Got it.
Liquor-store owner just ID'd Sol
Negro, a.k.a. Julio Gallegos...
...as our shooter in
that Christmas robbery.
If we close any more cases
because of Otilio's songs...
...we should deputize him.
Maybe I can get him to write a
tune about my cuddler rapist.
- You coming?
- Can't.
One dead woman had a friend's
number in her pocket.
She should be here any minute.
That's Leticia.
She was my best friend in Mexico.
Her body was found along
with seven others...
...all showing signs of
long-term chemical exposure.
What kind of chemical?
The kind they use to
make methamphetamines.
She would have had to breathe an
awful lot to die of exposure.
She never touched drugs.
- When did she come to L.A.?
- I don't know.
She saved up for a coyote
to bring her up...
...but I never saw her.
She called me two weeks ago,
but I only got a message.
Saying what?
That she needed help.
But then it hung up.
And you didn't report her missing?
To who? To say what?
That she was being smuggled over
the border and needed help?
Sol Negro. Spelled
just like it sounds.
- Any problems?
- Piece of cake.
Gonna jump back on the cuddler case.
I need some help. Hit a wall
ID'ing some of the other bodies.
So, what, we're just gonna drop all
of our other cases, is that it?
Eight dead women doesn't
fire your engine?
I don't wanna lose momentum on
the rape case. I can't do both.
- Fine, just give me a second.
- Thanks.
- Otilio. Otilio!
- Buzz me, buzz me.
You guys all right?
Get him to the ER, make
sure they take an x-ray.
- What was that guy saying?
- There's your next song.
Tell me I'm rich again.
I can't crack it.
Well, can you pull the lock out?
- Not so you wouldn't notice.
- This keeps getting better.
How do we get the safe back
inside with Aceveda still here?
Let's worry about the list first.
Got one window, and in about three
hours it's gonna slam shut.
We'll each take turns
tracking Aceveda's movements.
- Smitty could get in the safe.
- No.
Wanna keep this in-house
until we absolutely have to.
Shit.
- I'm really busy, Mara.
- Guess who I was on the phone with.
- Can we talk about this later?
- She calls me in a panic.
It's always the same old shit.
Mom says that they're gonna kick
her out of her apartment...
...if I can't help her with the rent.
I haven't sold a single house yet.
We'll talk about it
later, okay, baby?
Later when?
Are you ever coming home?
I really need you.
I'll be back as soon as I can, okay?
Hey, Dutch, we have to
do the annual inventory.
- Lucky you.
- Yeah.
Listen, did you check out a
departmental laptop computer...
- ...about 10 months ago?
- No.
According to this, you did.
A Dell 5100.
Whatever you're looking
at, it's wrong.
Is that your signature?
Yeah.
Good work out there today.
Thank Boris.
Yeah, I saw him out there.
Seemed a little restless.
He's frustrated. He's worked
up and wants to go all night.
Corpus interruptus.
One of these days we're gonna
meet under better circumstances.
Why leave it to chance?
Why isn't the
narcocorrido in the cage?
I don't know. I could check
the logbook if you want.
Then you go get it.
I gotta get Koto.
Narcotics called, said
that they wanted him to...
...sniff out an after-hours club.
- Good luck.
- Okay, see you.
Where's Chaydez and the singer?
We had to cut them loose.
Christ.
Cut them loose after I
told her to keep them?
His hold time was over.
Had no choice.
You think you can disobey
a direct goddamn order?
He didn't.
I did.
You?
We have to protect the case.
I don't think you
realize how long we...
I realize that I am
still captain here.
And I will not put up with
shit like this again.
Hey, did you find that computer yet?
- No, not yet. Did you?
- No.
If you don't locate it,
city's gonna bill you.
Yeah.
I did remember what
I was using it for.
- What?
- Child porn.
I had some downtime, so I was
going into local chat rooms...
...websites, see if anybody was
peddling smut or trying to lure kids.
And I got drawn into something
else, forgot about it.
So when we find this computer that
was last signed out by you...
...it's gonna be loaded
up with kiddie porn?
Yeah, I would appreciate a
chance to delete any files...
...before anybody gets a look.
I swear it was just work.
Nina, my guys need some new
things for the clubhouse.
Could you cut through some red tape?
You have to submit a request
to each department.
Everybody knows you need
something done, come to you.
I've got my own emergency
to deal with right now.
Maybe I can help.
Not unless you're a
licensed locksmith.
Locksmith? Smitty's your guy.
I have one. Thanks, thank you.
Hector Moreno? Please.
Try Pelican Bay.
He got sent up on a
burglary eight months ago.
We've used Smitty before.
But, hey, you know what you're doing.
I'm sorry.
Is this Smitty person nearby?
Why are we meeting in
the back of a van?
We need a little help
getting into a safe.
Listen, guys, I'm kind of turning over
a new leaf, you know what I mean?
- Yeah, it's about time.
- Sounds like a good idea.
I gotta be kind of selective
about the jobs I take.
- I'm gearing up a new business now.
- Home security, right?
Hit a little start-up gift for you.
Home burglaries in Farmington
over the last two months...
...plus addresses and phone numbers.
You say hello to 150 sure things.
First things first.
I'm gonna need the combination.
- This could take a while.
- Just get it open.
Let me know when you get in.
- Yeah.
- Five, nine, five.
Five, four, six.
All right, make a copy of the
list, get it back here quick.
Aceveda's got other stuff here.
Forget them, just get the list.
Come on, come on, come on.
- Got it.
- Go. Go, baby, go.
Came from the bank.
Chaydez cleaned out his
account when the bank opened.
- Who's on him now?
- Walon. Chaydez had an account...
...in two names. The teller
ID'd the Maldonado girl.
- Reina? When did she see her?
- About a week ago.
She's alive? The teller's
sure it was the same girl?
She remembers because they
seemed like an odd couple.
She seemed too old to be his daughter
and too young to be his girlfriend.
Reina was seen a week ago.
I knew it. I knew she was alive.
How well did she and
Chaydez know each other?
Not well.
Chaydez worked for my husband.
Tiling.
I knew he was hanging
around her too much.
Could they have been
closer than you think?
No.
- Her papa would have killed her.
- What if Reina kept it a secret?
She was 14.
She don't keep a secret
like that from me.
No.
No, wait. Hang on, he's coming back.
- Activity at Chaydez's house.
- What kind?
- Where is he now?
- In and out of his garage.
He's unloading something
out of his van.
- What's he taking out?
- Boxes and a bunch of bags.
Something that looks
like wire or rope.
- He's ready to move something.
- No sign of the girl?
- Nothing.
- Stay on him.
What if she's the thing being moved?
Any way to see inside?
The shades are drawn.
What about the back?
- Same thing.
- Go in.
- What?
He could be prepping
to kill her right now.
If he's got her stashed someplace
else, we might never find her.
And any evidence we find
might be thrown out.
We can give him a few more minutes.
I said, go in, get the girl.
No sign of her?
Some clothes, shoes. She was
there for a while at some point.
Any proof she's still alive?
Found a receipt for some
makeup bought three days ago.
It's not admissible. Nothing will be.
We don't know that for sure.
We went inside in good faith.
We have to assume it's no good.
So we can't even get him on
playing house with a minor?
We found her clothes
in your apartment.
- A receipt dated a week ago.
- I haven't seen her.
The bank teller remembers you two
opening an account together.
That's a problem, seeing
how you're on probation...
- ...for one statutory rape.
- You got something against pubes?
I didn't do anything wrong.
As you see it. You're in love.
- Yeah.
- Forget the fact...
...she's barely out of algebra.
You're connected to the dead women.
We'll find out how.
What I still wanna know is
what happened to Reina.
It's just one more.
- You help us, maybe we can help you.
- I see how you liked her.
Uncomplicated.
Too inexperienced to see
what a xxxx you really are.
I liked her, but I wouldn't be
with her. Her parents were crazy.
She was 14.
You tell the mom I had
something to do with it...
...and she comes by my place.
That's why he wrote the song, right?
To get the parents off your back?
- It's just a song.
- I'm talking to you.
Look at me.
I liked her.
- She liked me.
- Enough to go to prison for her?
Or did you hate the mom so much
you made the song come true?
I got it.
She's not a victim, she loves me.
Hey! Hey, enough!
Enough. Enough!
You sit down there,
keep your mouth shut.
I had to put a new door on.
Here's the combination.
Write him a check.
All right, enough...
Ever see her before?
She died. Of chemical-meth exposure.
She had a phone number on her.
We checked the records, found out
she used your phone to call it.
Maybe I dialed the wrong number.
And left a message doing
an impression of her?
I have a few cell phones.
I don't keep track of
them all the time.
- What kind of work do you do?
- Whatever I can, whenever I can.
You trying to pass yourself
off as a migrant worker?
I'm from Sinaloa.
We are migrants.
Nice threads.
Must have found better work than
picking strawberries in Oxnard.
Now, she was found with traces of lye
and red phosphorus in her lungs.
She worked in a meth lab.
- Horrible.
- Bullshit.
She worked in your meth
lab, she used your phone.
I don't think so.
Vic, Chaydez give you anything?
Nothing.
Hey, thanks for taking all
the heat with Aceveda.
- Where is he now?
- He had to run out.
Baodelo was arrested in Sinaloa
last year for manufacturing meth.
No conviction. Not even a
trial, but he was arrested.
What did you expect, the
policía to be honest?
I expect them to at least pretend.
Makes three dead ends we've hit.
Chaydez, Baodelo and the narco.
- Your guy know our guy?
- I don't think so. Why?
Because Chaydez is
chewing his ear off.
Maybe our two cases are related.
Hey, Dutch, I understand you
lost a department computer?
I saw it missing on
their inventory report.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Still haven't located it?
No, not yet, but it'll turn up.
Well, just so you know,
I had to call IAD.
- Excuse me?
- They're gonna have to investigate.
Any missing city property
valued at over $500...
...has to be investigated by IAD.
I just wanted to warn you.
- Smitty do you right?
- Yes, thank you.
Sorry, Dutch boy.
Please tell me you
put her up to that.
I didn't. I'm sorry.
We'll find it.
- Hey, I'm coming home soon.
- I'm bleeding.
- It's the baby.
- Bleeding? Are you sitting down?
- No.
- Sit.
- Did you call your doctor?
- No, I called you.
Page her. Tell them
it's an emergency.
- Shane, our baby.
- Call the doctor, all right?
Lie down. I'm on my
way home right now.
Got something.
Our boys Chaydez and Baodelo
are second cousins.
So Chaydez finds out about his
cousin's meth-lab cemetery...
...possibly helps him
bury the bodies.
Then passes one along
to Otilio for the song.
Any thoughts on how to get our killing
cousins to turn against each other?
Maybe we should take it to the press.
Not only is Reina not buried by the
tracks, she's not buried at all.
She's alive. So much for
your journalistic integrity.
But I saw a body.
And now you just admitted
to being an accessory.
No. No, I didn't.
Chaydez had a second cousin
in the meth business.
Somehow all his workers seem to
end up dead. That's who you saw.
Thought you were supposed
to get facts right.
That makes you a fraud.
How's that gonna play
down in the barrio?
Thought you guys were supposed
to be all about the truth.
I thought it was the truth.
Yeah, well, I'm gonna make sure
everybody knows it wasn't.
We wouldn't want your fans...
...paying good money
for a corrido con job?
They talking?
Chaydez can't keep his mouth shut.
Trish took a bath in
Southern Comfort.
Gotta say, she commits.
Let's hope her Spanish is as
good as her homeless routine.
Chaydez told the truth, the whole
truth, and kept telling the truth.
He's hiding her at a friend's.
Name's Joaquin.
We'll find the friend.
Also said his cousin runs his
meth lab out of a truck.
Right now it's in an industrial
park in Boyle Heights.
Go.
Okay, let's get the trailer open.
Hazardous fumes. Don't
breathe inside the trailer.
Welcome to the land of promise.
Come be our slave.
Yeah, heard that one before.
Chaydez?
Hello, Reina.
We're here to rescue you.
All right, you're gonna wait here.
Do I have to see her now?
Yeah, you do.
Sit down.
Reina's safe. She's safe, she's okay.
Where is she?
She's inside.
But there's something I
gotta tell you first.
She went away with
Chaydez on her own.
What? No.
She knew that you and your
husband would never approve.
Pero the funeral.
- She didn't come.
- Well, she's young.
She thought she was in love.
She made a mistake.
No.
You're wrong.
She's still your daughter.
Reina's only 15. She made a mistake.
Let her fix it. She needs to see you.
No, not now.
Look familiar, you big perv?
- Where was it?
- Desk drawer in the storage room.
Also found your renewal card for
Tiger Beat. I mailed it in.
Funny later, not funny now.
You're back.
Yeah, I had this odd feeling I
made a mistake in my paperwork.
- You never made one before.
- Well, you can't be too sure.
Maybe you were just
hoping you'd run into me.
There is a difference between
confidence and overconfidence.
Boyfriend cooking for you tonight?
He works weekends.
I can throw parsley on a
plate with the best of them.
- It's a bad idea.
- Name one bad thing about it.
I'm involved.
Mentally, you're already checked out.
What makes you say that?
I'll explain it over dinner.
What do you have to
go back to work for?
It's just for a couple hours. We're
just finishing something up.
I'm having a miscarriage
and you're leaving.
It's just spotting. Doc says
everything's gonna be all right.
But you gotta take it easy.
You gotta take care of our baby.
Now, you sure you don't need
anything else before I go?
Just for you to stay.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
I promise.
Bye-bye.
She should know.
Wanna try to draw the
house like this?
That's not bad.
Hey, guys.
Can we watch a movie tonight, Daddy?
Maybe. What's going on?
Can I talk to you for a second?
Sure.
Hi, honey.
- Hey, sis.
- It's okay.
- Can I ask a favor?
- What?
Can you take the kids this weekend?
I don't have them until next weekend.
- Please.
- Why?
I have some things I
have to do and I am....
I don't want them to be
around me like this.
Has something happened?
Is it your mother?
No.
Did you know it would be this hard?
This empty?
I didn't know what it would be.
I'm having a hard time.
Can you take the kids this weekend?
- I really don't want them to...
- Sure, sure.
- I'll take them next weekend.
- That's okay, I miss them.
Okay, great.
I'm gonna be all right.
Okay.
I'm sorry, I can't do tonight.
- Everything okay?
- Better offer.
Two nights with my kids.
It's probably a sign.
- It's a scheduling snafu. Next week?
- No, it feels like a sign.
Maybe we'll catch another
case again together sometime.
We made the case against Chaydez.
Found Reina.
Good.
- What's this?
- lnterrogation-room tape from today.
You cut me a break when I
went off the grid for Tommy.
- Can't stand owing you something.
- Dad, let's go.
I'm coming, baby.
Hey, Rigo.
There a family reunion
I didn't know about?
How you doing, man?
You all right?
- What, and you couldn't stop them?
- He had a gun to my head.
- You couldn't do anything?
- What would you have done?
- Does Aurora know?
- Nobody knows.
Man, all I wanted to do was survive.
See my wife and....
See my wife and my little girl again.
And now all I do is make
up excuses not to go home.
You did what you had to do.
No one can blame you.
I went after a suspect today.
And I kicked the shit out of him.
The only thing that stopped me was...
...I started to piss my pants.
I'm losing control of everything.
Then take it back.
I don't know how.
You're a captain.
You command 200 men.
Hell, you're gonna be the
next city councilman.
You have power, David.
You have a gun and a badge.
Now, these were just a
couple of punk assholes.
Do you know who they are?
I could find out.
But even then, what?
If it was me, I'd kill them.