Previously on "The Shield".
Known this girl for two months,
you're buying a new car?
- What's the problem?
- This thing between me and Vic...
Sometimes brothers fight.
So why is he always making
you the little brother?
Did I do something to piss you off?
I don't like the way you treat Shane.
You don't understand the world
that Shane and I live in.
Shane works for you, but
he comes home to me.
You said you had a few ideas
about adding personnel?
The undercover Decoy
Squad working Wilshire.
I need someone overseeing the
practical elements of my plan.
Your plan?
David's bringing in the
Decoy Squad from Wilshire.
They're gonna be working with you.
I'm gonna be in charge of both teams.
They killed these Armenians
looking for our money-train cash.
There's four people who
know we took that money.
They're all sitting right here.
Stick to the plan.
You need to go somewhere.
- You need help.
- I'll get clean.
- You can get me through it.
- Jesus Christ, Connie.
I can't be helped.
- You're cleaned.
- Yeah.
This is the C.I. contract.
Calm down.
- Jesus Christ!
- Shut up!
What the hell is the matter with you?
Vic, I'm sorry.
Yo, what's up, boss?
Seen the new 20?
- Yeah, man. The colours are funky.
- Yeah.
The old ones are gonna be phased out
of the system over the next year.
So, what about our money-train 20s?
We have to unload our 20s
sooner than we wanted to...
...before they stand out too much.
Shit.
So Claudette's in
charge of our team now?
- That's the way she sees it.
- You had a female boss before?
You ever met my daughter?
- She's insisting we go mini-putting.
- So how do we deal with her?
Kill her with kindness.
Couple of months, we'll
get our freedom back.
It's not like we can't use the break.
Catching those preppy lawyers
with their pants down.
I think you guys got the wrong room.
Wyms told us to shack up here.
We're the Decoy Squad.
We just transferred in.
- I'm Walon. Eddie, Annie, Trish.
- Vic Mackey.
It's crowded in here. Why
don't I talk to my captain...
...see if I can scrounge
you up some new digs?
- Seems okay to me.
- Yeah, we can make it work.
Man, what's that smell?
I've been playing homeless
for the last three days.
Kind of ripe?
- Where's the shower around here?
- First door on the left.
- Look, I need to go to work.
- Then go already.
Well, I don't wanna leave arguing.
What's the problem?
Nothing.
Look, what are you doing? This
doesn't have to be a thing.
You don't want me here.
Look, I said I thought it was a
little fast for you to be moving in.
It doesn't mean that I don't
want you here when I get home.
Shit. Hey.
- What, couldn't find the shower?
- Yeah, I found it. Thanks.
Where's the rest of your team?
I gave Ronnie a pass. He's seeing
a plastic surgeon about his face.
- And Shane?
- Car battery died. He'll meet us.
Okay, our first target, prostitution.
We've mapped out four
key red-light zones.
Phase one, get the girls off the
street. Phase two, nail the johns.
A temporary processing station's
been set up to expedite arrests.
Also, media crews will be filming
to discourage offenders...
...and anyone watching
from ever coming back.
The DA's office has
been helpful as well.
Members of your team can now
show their members to the girls.
- We get to show our dxxxs?
- Time to pull out the pipes, fellas.
It's only to convince them that
you're not law enforcement.
They can look, they can't touch.
Their loss.
- Chicken-head, 2 o'clock.
- Drive-through blowjobs.
- All right, I'm rolling up.
- We got you, good buddy.
- You looking for a date?
- It's too nice a night to be lonely.
- You a cop?
- I look like a cop?
Yeah. Let me see your package.
You gotta promise not
to get scared away.
- Go ahead, frighten me.
- Okay.
Halloween's early this year.
Want some candy?
Well, how do I know you're not a cop?
I am a cop. See my badge?
Go, brother.
That just made my week.
Head's 50, sex is 75,
anal's a hundred.
- Hey. Sorry.
- You wanna be my backdoor baby?
- Where the hell you been?
- Just dealing with some stuff.
Next time, pick up a phone
or at least answer yours.
Hey, we got an assault in progress.
You guys see that?
Lem, hit it.
- Police!
- I'm okay.
- Get off!
- Here. Come here.
- I got the runner.
- Get off me, you bastard!
- Freeze! Police!
- You're under arrest, princess.
All right, ladies. Easy.
- Just relax.
- My arm!
All right, everybody calm down.
Hey, I know you, right?
- No.
- Yeah.
You're the cop that was there
when Connie got killed.
I saw you at the funeral.
I was her friend.
You were too, right?
What do you want?
My pimp kicked me out on the street,
won't let anyone else take me in.
I got no protection.
Well, it looks like it's
time to relocate then...
...or find a new line of work.
- Please, I just...
- Sorry.
Connie said you helped her, said
you looked out for her and Brian.
Look, Connie was just
an informant of mine.
So dropping her name
is doing you no good.
- I heard you helped her out.
- You heard wrong.
Please. You're a cop. They're
gonna kill me out there.
Do something for me.
I'm not gonna judge
the life you chose...
...but I'm not gonna get
sucked into it either.
Good luck.
My. You two dirty up quite nicely.
This? Just a few rags from my closet.
I'll give you a runway show sometime.
She's not kidding.
These are hers too.
All these arrests are
for solicitation?
Assault and battery.
Buys us an extra three to
six months off the street.
Sorry to set the bar so
high your first night.
-Well, we'll see if we can keep up.
-Thanks for coming.
Yeah, I had a flat. I got
there as quick as I could.
I told her your battery died.
It was personal. It
won't happen again.
I talked to the hooker who got jumped.
She'll build a case against her pimp.
I talked to her too. She's a liar.
Then she should fit
right in on your team.
Work with her. I've sent a
message to the gals and johns...
...and I'd like to send
one to the pimps too.
You're the boss.
- Thought you had that hooker sting?
- It's in motion.
I heard you got a call.
Thought I'd check in.
Victim's name is lsabel
Nelson, raped by a lone male.
Guy was waiting in the house
naked when she came home.
Left with jewellery, a little cash.
- Is that her?
- That's her daughter.
Isabel's 73.
- He had a ski mask covering his head.
- Was he black, white?
White, maybe Mexican, not black.
Do you remember anything
about his body?
Tattoos, birthmarks, anything?
All I saw was his....
And it didn't look anything
like my husband's used to look.
Well, we can talk about this later.
I wanna help. He shouldn't
have done this.
Is it true that he
didn't leave right away?
He wanted to know where my
jewellery was, and he took it.
Then he laid down on the
bed again, next to me...
...he put his hands on
me, two or three hours.
- Was he holding you down?
- No.
He just....
Cuddled with you.
That was the worst part.
It's okay. Good.
Would you stop ignoring my messages
and call me back? Okay? Please?
- Trouble in paradise.
- That's one I won't miss.
What's up?
I'm sorry I went over your head.
I didn't know she was your boss.
You just don't understand
how dangerous Smooth is.
I know pimps. Only thing original
about them are their names.
- Where are you from?
- San Jose.
When this is over, why don't you
take a bus, open up shop there?
I like L.A.
Smooth will kill you if he
finds out you helped us.
Not if you protect me.
Let's be clear.
This is a one-shot deal,
sweetie, then we're done.
The guy in the suit, what's he in on?
Solicitation. Won't give
his name, had no ID.
Nothing at all?
Ass Invader? I've been looking all
over Beverly Hills for one of those.
Somebody dropped by the store,
said, "Give me one of everything."
He has got a dildo in there
you could snake a drain with.
I'll handle this one. Finish
the paperwork, run it by me.
Captain's real hands-on here?
You could say that.
See anything in there
I should take home?
- How are you, David?
- Better than you, Javier.
That policewoman made a big mistake.
I don't wanna get anybody
in trouble, but,...
...you know, she's acted out of line.
How?
She flagged me over, said
she wanted directions.
I'm not out there looking
for this, so help me.
Come on, Javier, I saw the
bag you were arrested with.
Embarrassing, it's not illegal.
- Why didn't you give your name?
- I panicked.
I'm trying to save the
district from scandal.
For God's sake, do you know
what would happen to me...
...if people think I
actually did this?
So why cuddle?
Is that a guilt reaction or some
kind of emotional souvenir?
"Just because I raped you doesn't
mean we can't be friends"?
Thanks for the assignment.
- Farrah's a real winner.
- What'd she give us?
Smooth's running a glorified
whorehouse for downtown suits.
He keeps a drug stash in the house in
case his guests need a pick-me-up.
- You know, X, oxy, coke.
- I'll call for a warrant.
You see if Shane slept
through his alarm.
All right, that's the target.
The drug stash is in
the last bedroom.
Tavon's got point.
- Tavon? What about me?
- You got one strike with Claudette.
If something goes wrong, I
don't want you taking a hit.
- Well, why would something go wrong?
- It won't.
- It's on.
- Okay. Give up your hardware.
Farrah says they're running clients
for metal on the way inside,...
...so give it up.
Okay, you're not packing, so keep
it simple. Get in, get solicited.
Shane will call in the signal.
- Who's Smooth's bottom bitch?
- She's the queen whore, Cocoa.
- So how'd you hear about us?
- We came in for the car convention.
The boys from Chevy
gave me your number.
- Who do you like?
- What about you?
You can get the mouth, but
only Smooth gets my booty.
- Suck you bone-dry for a hundred.
- Hope you're worth it.
- Now, that's mine.
- Party favours?
- Coke? X? Viagra?
- I'll take some X.
And get my boy here some of that
Viagra. He can use the boost.
Follow me.
- You got a bathroom?
- Upstairs.
I'm gonna give you something
more than you bargained for.
Hey, it's a go. Two guys packing
just inside the front door.
Go. Move. Come on, move your ass.
- Go.
- My God!
Shit, it's reinforced.
The door is holding.
Open it from the inside.
- I got it.
- Get out of the way!
It's a raid!
- Where the hell's backup?
- Can't get in.
- Get out, girls!
- Hey, get her, man.
Let us out there!
Police! Freeze!
- Where's Tavon?
- She's flushing the drugs!
Get down! Get out of here right now!
Get out!
- Can we get a ram in here?
- Hurry up!
- Get the ram!
- Here, come here, come here!
Go, go!
- Too late.
- Get on your feet!
Hands on your head! Get against
the wall. Turn to the wall!
- Yes?
- I'm Detective Wagenbach.
I'm investigating a break-in
at the building next door.
- You notice anyone unusual?
- Just the police.
What about your family?
It's just me and my son
Josh, but he wasn't home.
- How old is Josh?
- Nineteen.
I'm gonna need to talk to him.
Have him give me a call.
That's my number if you
think of something else.
Should I be worried?
That was a lot of
commotion for a break-in.
Just make sure you lock up
when you're not at home.
Thank you. Excuse me.
Smooth's smarter than
we gave him credit for.
They registered his
cathouse in Cocoa's name.
Summer classes at Pimp U paid off.
Well, she's so brainwashed,
she'll never roll on him.
Without a drug charge to hold over...
What are you saying?
Everyone but King
Shithead gets busted?
Looks like it's time for
you to catch that bus.
I didn't do this so he could walk.
And I didn't do this to settle
some personal grudge of yours.
We got his house, his bottom
bitch, most of his girls.
- It was a good day.
- No.
Use me if you have to.
That cocksucker turned out
my 13-year-old sister...
...when she came to visit me.
Got her shooting up. Next
thing, she's hooking.
- Then she gets sick.
- AIDS?
I haven't seen her in two months.
Who knows who she's sucking
off for pocket change.
- Don't let him keep doing this.
- What do you think?
- Her half-assed sob story?
- No. Using her to get to Smooth.
Could get her killed. If she
doesn't care, why should we?
We send her out of
town when it's done.
I say we move on to the next
thing, get her out of our lives.
The reason pimp cases are impossible
is because girls won't cooperate.
She's willing. I say we go with it.
- Saddle someone else with it.
- I'm saddling you.
Look, you want Smooth, I
want my clubhouse back.
This isn't a barter,
it's an assignment.
Everyone's saying
Mrs. Nelson was raped.
Ma'am, we don't discuss
ongoing cases.
Look, I'm alone a lot
when my son's out...
...and I asked you if
I should be worried.
Paul Fets, have you talked with him?
- He's raped before.
- Paul Fets?
He's a registered sex offender, lives
across the street from Mrs. Nelson.
Why am I the one checking on this?
Ma'am, there are 34
registered sex offenders...
...in the five-block area
around that apartment...
...including 12 high-risk felons.
Fets followed me into
my apartment once...
...said he wanted to
help with my groceries.
If my son hadn't come home right
then, it would've been me.
Well, we will talk to him.
He was looking in her window...
...Mrs. Nelson's, about a week ago.
I caught him.
Why didn't you tell
me that this morning?
Because you didn't tell me you
were looking for a rapist.
Did you hear there was a woman raped
in the building next to yours?
No.
Somebody crawled into her window,
raped her when she came home.
Sounds a lot like that
trouble you got into before.
Sorry I'm late. Hello.
Mandy Trujillo.
She was a paraplegic
girl in a wheelchair.
You forced her side door open...
...went into her bedroom, put your
thing in her mouth, didn't you?
I don't think that way anymore.
Well, maybe you can explain...
...why somebody saw you looking
into Mrs. Nelson's window?
- The same window the rapist went in?
- That wasn't me.
Was she home? Or did you decide
to come back when she was gone?
I didn't look through her window.
And you didn't follow Wanda Ledda
into her apartment either, did you?
I was trying to help her
with the groceries.
She didn't have to tell the
neighbours about me. I...
I don't like that pressure.
Be here by 10 in the morning,
we'll take a run at your pimp.
Why can't we do it tonight?
Because you're not the only woman
in my life who needs attention.
- Well, where am I supposed to stay?
- Where'd you stay last night?
My place. But it's not safe there.
Just give me some money for a motel.
I already gave you a bus ticket.
Feel free to use it any time.
Just call me and tell me you're okay.
Could you do that, please?
Great goddamn day.
First Mara, then I gotta
share a locker with Pig-Pen.
- They'll be gone soon.
- Yeah, or we will.
They made 15 arrests last night.
- So, what's with Mara?
- These pimps have it figured out.
You treat them like shit,
they stick to you like flies.
If only swatting them
away was as easy.
I just don't wanna
swat this one away.
It's the first girl I've been
with that's better than me.
She's not better than you.
She's probably just
blowing off steam.
- Yeah.
- Just give her some space.
She'll call you.
You going out?
Yeah, I got my daughter tonight.
Mini-putt and ice cream.
- That's good, man.
- Yeah.
Be nice to get away
from all the drama.
Mom.
I'm sorry, I don't
know what happened.
- She kept screaming to come home.
- Go get ready for bed.
I want Daddy to tuck me in.
- Go to your room.
- No.
Listen to your mother. I'll make
it up to you next week, I promise.
No, Daddy, please stay.
- Jesus.
- Cassidy, stop this right now.
Well, hold on. Maybe I should
stay, just for an hour.
Cassidy come here right now.
Get over here. Listen to me.
I know what you're doing, and
it's not going to work, okay?
Your father's going to leave now.
If you wanna spend time with him...
...you will behave when it's his
turn to see you. Now, let's go.
No, Daddy, please don't go.
- Go.
- Please, Daddy, don't go!
- Dad, don't. Please.
- Go!
- Dad, please don't.
As you can imagine, I deal
with rape and death every day.
- I'm sorry.
- I don't mind. Feel like I'm helping.
Like I'm taking bad people away
before they can hurt somebody else.
That's not me.
In my experience, people who would...
...rape an old woman
or a crippled lady...
...they always do it again.
You do know that, right?
You know what a moral compass is?
It's a thing in people that tells
them what's right and what's wrong.
They know because this
moral compass guides them.
Only it gets broken in
some people, smashed.
So they do these horrible things,
but it's not their fault.
Their compass is just broken.
Can I go to the bathroom?
- Sure.
- No, this is for girls.
The men's is broken.
It's all right, everybody
uses this one.
I did things.
I know.
What...? All right, what if
your moral compass is broken?
How do you fix it?
You can't.
Isabel, that old woman...
...this is the last sexual
experience she's gonna have.
I mean, can you even imagine that?
A grandmother. Imagine if
it were your grandmother.
I don't think you wanna
hurt anybody again...
...but you gotta help me make
sure that doesn't happen.
- I don't wanna be broken.
- Okay.
Okay.
- Javier send you?
- What are we going to do?
I don't think there's
much we can do, Jorje.
Sanchez is a friend.
- Of yours.
- He's been supportive of you.
Letting him go without processing
while I look into things...
...is as supportive as I can be.
He told me it was entrapment.
Is it possible?
I plan on talking to
the arresting officer.
I remember when a reporter was
asking questions about you once...
...about the rape at USC.
I didn't rape anyone.
- She was an unstable woman.
- Yeah, but I supported you.
And I never asked you
if it was true or not.
Tell me about the Sanchez arrest.
He pulled up to the curb.
- Did you flag him?
- I smiled at him.
- I do have a nice smile.
- Then what?
I engaged him. He said the magic
words, I gave the signal.
- Be more specific.
- He's into pegging.
He said he wanted to do me
with his favourite dildo...
...then have me strap one
on and return the favour.
Offered me 150 bucks,
the cheap bastard.
- I've had men go as high as five.
- He's claiming it was entrapment.
Did you see his bag?
Bondage is more like it.
I'm still looking into this case.
Don't discuss it with anyone.
Hey, you guys took a call at L.A.
Sound Design last week?
- The one on Sixth Street?
- Yeah.
Just took one at the
store on Olympic.
I asked the owner for
his surveillance...
...he goes in the back
for two minutes,...
...comes out, the tape is ruined.
Ours didn't have a camera.
Two in two weeks.
Hey, can I get a copy of the
serial numbers you guys took?
Isn't that for the insurance
company to worry about?
Yeah, but the detectives
are short-staffed.
It's low priority. I was thinking
maybe we can sniff around on our own.
Just because you been
on the sidelines...
...doesn't mean you have
to play Wonder Woman.
Though I might be able to
dig up the outfit for you.
The call didn't seem right to me.
We filed our paperwork.
Yeah, there was nothing weird that
I can remember about the call.
Fine.
Sorry to interrupt your dinner.
Hey, Danny.
Give me half an hour, and I'll
pull it all together for you.
Thanks.
Keep it simple. Turn around.
Tell him you want back into his
stable, you'll do whatever it takes.
- I asked him before.
- Most of his girls are in lockup.
Chances are he'll need temps.
Can't wait to see his
face when we bust him.
Well, if he gets
rough, I'll stop him.
I can handle a beating.
You won't have to.
Bury it.
- Don't touch me.
- Come on.
Like you never took a
free suck from Connie.
We can help each other.
Just put on the goddamn wire.
She said you were nice.
All you've ever been
to me is a jerk.
Place the wire and follow me.
Dutch got a confession
from the rapist.
That's great news.
Hey, just curious.
We arrested 15 johns
yesterday, but only booked 14.
- I released one.
- Now I'm even more curious.
Javier Sanchez is the
superintendent of schools.
I'm double-checking the
facts before proceeding.
His facts couldn't be
checked from the cage?
I'm extending him a courtesy.
What qualifies as the
special-treatment club this week?
As soon as he's processed,
he'll be publicly humiliated.
His career, effectively,
will be over.
I was under the impression
we were showing people...
- ...that things were changing here.
- We are.
Smells like the same cooking to me.
You made all of these arrests
in the last hour? Good work.
Finish the handoff then
get back out there.
We keep hauling in this many fish...
...we might need to
find you new digs.
- We set?
- Yeah, just waiting for your okay.
Yeah?
Where have you been?
Look, you understand that
once you go in there...
...your life's at stake.
- Yes.
- You're gonna have to get on the bus.
- I will.
- Look, I gotta go.
We're in the middle
of something here.
I'm sorry. Look, I
need a personal day.
Not a problem.
Look who crawled out
from under its rock.
Can we talk?
- You got nothing to say, bitch.
- I'll work twice as hard.
- I'll be your best earner.
- I said you have nothing to say.
Gotta go.
Hold on.
You go out, hit it hard enough
tonight, maybe we'll talk.
You freak on me again, I'll kill you.
It's good.
We got it on tape. Good job.
These turn into
bruises, get Polaroids.
Yep.
Can I get your opinion on something?
I'd stick with the fishnets.
French maid's outfit
might be too much.
I got stuck between Claudette
and Aceveda on something.
What exactly are the
politics around here?
Tell me more.
That john I brought in
with the goodie bag.
Seems like Aceveda
wants it to go away.
- Important guy, I guess.
- Claudette has another idea.
So push comes to shove,
which pony would you ride?
Aceveda's still the boss.
After that, city council.
If he asks for something,
do him the favor.
Thanks.
You like Chinese?
Sometimes.
I'll take you to Chinese
sometime, pay you back.
- Fets didn't cuddle.
- What?
In his statement, he says...
...he raped her, then left. He can't
tell me anything about the jewellery.
Says he dumped it but
doesn't remember where.
We've got a confession.
We got a witness who
saw him at the window.
He is slow.
This is a guy who raped a woman,
didn't leave a single hair fiber.
Now, not only have I been
chasing the wrong guy...
...I caught him.
Give Smooth the money. Be very
clear you earned it hooking.
That's like $600. It's not enough.
You've been at it a couple of hours.
- He won't take this. It's an insult.
- Make it work. It's all we have.
He'll kill me if I
give him this little.
We're not gonna let him hurt you.
No. I'll just tell him.
I'll just go and explain.
- You won't explain anything.
- I'll tell him I changed my mind.
- You tell him that, he will kill you.
- Let go of me.
You don't give a shit about me!
You're bastard!
- He'll take care of me if I tell him.
- Don't do it.
I'm not doing this.
You think you could
just walk away from me?
Get off of me.
You made me a promise.
- You told me you wanted this.
- I don't wanna do this anymore.
Because you're scared?
- He'll kill me.
- You need to be scared of me.
- Vic...
- Back off!
Let me just go talk to him.
Take it! Now!
Smooth's my bitch...
...which makes you my bottom bitch.
You're gonna go out there, and
you're gonna do what I told you.
Or I swear to God, I will hurt you...
...like you've never been
goddamn hurt before.
You understand?
- Say it!
- Okay.
Good.
You wanna make me happy?
- Yes.
- I'm sure you do.
Okay.
Now...
...do what I told you.
Good girl. Go ahead.
- What the hell was that?
- I just saved her life. You watch.
- Rolled some tricks for you, baby.
- Slow your roll, ho.
Po-po's been cracking down.
Come here.
All right. Give up the skrilla.
- I can't see her.
- We're fine.
Petty cash. Where's the cheddar?
- Sucked a lot of dxxxs for that.
- You coming crooked on me?
It's all I got. You don't like it?
- Shove it up your ass.
- What's she doing?
Damn it, she's baiting him. Let's go.
Is that how it's gonna be?
- Punk ass, you're nothing.
- Yeah?
You don't scare me. Help! Let
go of me. I said let go of me.
Bastard!
Get back!
Stay still. Don't fight me.
I got marks. You can say he hit
me, get him put away longer.
I'm not lying. We got him for
what we got him on and that's it.
It'll be a long time before another
pimp thinks about laying a hand on me.
You forgetting about
that bus to San Jose?
I don't need it anymore.
You're protecting me.
No, I'm not. We're done now.
- Finished.
- Why are you such a shithead?
I chose you over Smooth.
I stopped you from killing yourself.
You stuck a gun in my mouth.
No, I did not.
- Now you're not gonna protect me?
- Shut up right now.
You're a bigger bastard than Smooth!
Bigger than the one who turned
out your 13-year-old sister?
- Right.
- I found out the only sister...
...you have is 7 and
living in San Jose.
You're just pissed off that
Smooth stopped you from earning.
Is that what you did to Connie too?
Used her?
She trusted you, and
you got her killed.
- Time to go.
- You dared that guy.
Her boy doesn't have a mother.
That's your fault.
- Wouldn't want you to miss your bus.
- You didn't give a shit about Connie!
I tolerated her to the extent
she could help me make cases.
She's dead because of you.
No.
You all find ways of
killing yourselves.
Go find yours.
Bastard!
- You call for backup?
- We got a hit on the stolen stereo.
A Sun Yun Do at this residence
registered online to get the warranty.
Sure you didn't wanna call SWAT?
You guys were so helpful
breaking this...
...I thought you'd wanna
be here for the arrest.
- What the hell are these?
- I went to see Isabel.
One of them's Fets.
You showed a 73-year-old
rape victim a xxxxx line-up?
She wants the guy caught.
All she saw was the xxxxx.
Plus, she picked the wrong one.
So whose did she choose?
Couldn't get anyone
else to volunteer.
Dutch.
Well, I didn't ask
you to look at them.
It's not anything you
haven't seen before.
The important thing is, Isabel
confirms that Fets isn't our guy.
We're sending you home.
Why?
Because you didn't rape Mrs. Nelson.
But I think about it. With other
women. Just like you said.
Still, you didn't do it.
No, my moral compass is broken.
Look, that was just an
interrogation technique.
I needed you to believe it
because I wanted you to confess.
Mandy Trujillo was seven years ago.
You've been good since then, right?
I tried real hard.
Well, and it's working. There's a Dr.
Lakeman...
...who's gonna come talk
to you about staying good.
I can't go home.
She told everybody about me.
And about Mandy.
Everybody hates me. She's gonna tell
them that I did it to that old woman.
I'll talk to your neighbors.
We're gonna catch the guy
who really did this.
Here's my card.
You call me if you need anything.
Anything.
You said you weren't gonna be here.
I wanted to see you for myself.
I'm just gonna get the rest of
my things then I'm leaving.
What is your problem?
Why are you acting like
such a psycho bitch?
Just leave me alone.
All right, fine. Fine.
You wanna leave?
Then pack your shit. Get out!
Here, better yet, let me help you.
Why are you sulking? You're
the one who turned on me.
That's not true.
So, what was the plan? You
couldn't afford a car?
So you give up a little ass, play
house till you can make your getaway?
- You're such a jerk.
- How's the Lexus driving?
Keep your goddamn car!
You keep it. You earned it.
Hope the next guy enjoys it.
Please, you gonna start crying now?
Let's see the floodgates open, Mara.
- Just let me go.
- No, I wanna see you cry first.
- Let me leave.
- No, I wanna see how you leaving me.
Tearing me...
I wanna see how it makes you cry.
I'm pregnant.
Bullshit.
I am.
It was an accident.
Sorry, okay? I'm sorry!
- Well, we'll get married.
- No!
God, help me.
Hey.
Hey. Look at me.
Marry me.
I had some more ideas on
your transition team.
So did Aurora.
Maybe we could get
together this week.
Thought you should know...
...Carlos Izturis from the
Daily News is downstairs.
- Hello.
- What does he want?
He is coming to ask about...
...Javier Sanchez being
arrested for solicitation.
- I know Carlos, I can talk to him.
- Good.
Tell him I'm moving
forward with the arrest.
- Give us a minute.
- Take a month...
...nothing's gonna change.
Send some unis to pick him up.
Nice seeing you again.
She leaked this. She
brought Izturis in.
The important thing is we cut
bait before Javier drags us down.
Dutch.
Hey. Congrats on your job back.
Thanks. Hey, thanks for
talking to Aceveda for me.
This is that case I
left the message about.
Yeah. Insurance thing, right?
Yeah. Guy's robbing from himself
then making the claims.
Sure makes it easier when officers
just hand me closed cases.
Just trying to help.
Detective, call for you on three.
Detective Wagenbach.
- I tried real hard.
- Hello?
Her son just left. She's alone.
- Paul?
- Finally got that bitch alone.
- Now you can stop me.
Paul, don't go anywhere, all right?
Let me talk to you.
- You have to stop me.
- Rape in progress. Call it in.
Paul, what are you feeling right now?
How do you change what you want?
It isn't what you want.
I promise you.
You've done so well.
No, I haven't. I'll try
not to hurt her too bad.
Paul? Paul...
Police! Open up!
- Police!
- Stop!
Stop!
Let me see your hands.
School and sex crimes.
That story's gonna hit big.
He brought it on himself.
You helped a little. I
know I didn't call Carlos.
Why would I call?
We're sending a message.
We're showing people
we're cracking down...
...and no one's safe in Farmington.
And you did it in a way that
didn't squash you and Machado.
You always were my best detective.
You looking for a date?
I want her.
She's not for sale.
That's Nasty's new girl.
How much to talk for two minutes?
Just wanna talk?
I see you missed that bus.
Figured I'd stay.
I know Nasty.
He's good at what he does. You
angling for him this whole time?
No. After you kicked
me, I had to survive.
Told Nasty I'd help him
get Smooth's girls.
So it's all my fault?
Thanks for helping make me queen.
Enjoy your kingdom.
That's 20 bucks.
I mean, I'm through the door, and all
I see is a black blur flying by me.
You're getting slow.
All I know is the rapist bastard got a
double dip of vanilla and chocolate.
Hey, Julien, you walking out?
Not yet.
All right. I'll see you tomorrow.
He knocked the wind out of him. We got
back here, he's still out of breath.
Wagenbach's upstairs.
- Congrats, man.
- Thank you, man.
- Thank you, buddy.
- Hey, man, where's Vic?
- Don't know, man.
- I'm gonna step outside for a second.
- All right. Okay.
Hey, Wayne. Beer's inside, buddy.
- Hey.
- Thank you.
You know where Vic is, man?
No clue.
Is this the foster home
for Brian Reisler?
- Yeah. Is there a problem?
- Can I see him?
Sure.
What's going on?
He wants to see Brian.
- How is he?
- What do you mean?
Is he talking yet? Making friends?
What's he like to do?
He plays with the other children.
How many foster children
do you have here?
Five.
Five hundred a head, that's
2500 you're pulling in a month.
Where's it all going?
You're saying we're skimping?
- They get what they need.
- Three hots and a cot?
- You bank the rest?
- What do you know about raising kids?
They're better off here
than they were out there.
How do you know that?
His mother was a crack whore.
I knew her.
Then you know what I'm talking about.
At least we're there for them.
I'm gonna be checking in
on him from time to time.
I better like what I see.