Previously on "The Shield".
I'm going back to work.
There's a nursing shortage,
and the pay is good.
How's that gonna work with the kids?
People are wondering what you're
doing about the beating you took.
Still can't prove who did it.
Everybody here knows who did it.
And they're watching you.
Julien, please!
I was thinking that we
both talk to Aceveda...
...about teaming up. It might
bring us back together.
Maybe but I like the
way things right now.
- I'm pregnant.
- Bullshit.
It was an accident.
- We'll get married.
- No!
Hey.
Marry me.
David's bringing in the
Decoy Squad from Wilshire.
They're gonna be working with you. I'm
gonna be in charge of both teams.
I think you guys got the wrong room.
Wyms told us to shack up here.
We're the Decoy Squad. We just
transferred in. I'm Walon.
Eddie, Annie, Trish.
- They'll be gone soon.
- Yeah, or we will.
They made 15 arrests last night.
We keep hauling in this many fish...
...we might need to
find you new digs.
You didn't hear, dude?
Shane's getting married.
Smokes for everyone.
Dutch.
This mean you're
coming off the market?
He's a family man now. He's gonna
be stuck at home with a rug rat.
You having a kid? Didn't
know you're married.
I'm not. Must've been an
immaculate conception.
Congratulations. Who is she?
She your cousin?
Vic.
Amazing thing is,
she's not a stripper.
How's Mara feeling?
She's got morning sickness already.
It's crazy, isn't it, man?
I'm gonna be a daddy.
Yeah.
Listen, we haven't talked plans.
I don't know, we may just elope.
But whatever we do, I want you there.
Absolutely.
Someone call for a detective?
That was me.
Mrs. Mackey? I didn't
know you worked here.
I just started. Corrine Mackey.
Dutch Wagenbach. Vic's wife?
Yeah, technically. Dr. Genty
asked me to call you.
- Hi.
- Doctor.
A patient came in with a bad
case of food poisoning.
- It's his third time this month.
- Fast food'll kill you.
Especially when it's
laced with thallium.
- Thallium. What's that?
- Poison.
Odorless, colorless, almost
impossible to detect.
Maybe someone's messing with
things at my grocery store.
We'll look into that.
Check other hospitals, see if they
have people with similar symptoms.
We need to make sure none of the
packages were tampered with.
Maybe it's a mix-up at the lab?
I mean, I feel better now.
We ran two different samples.
We have to ask, but...
Did you try to poison yourself?
God, no.
- No cell phones, please.
- Okay.
Where did you eat today?
Home. My brother stopped
by, we had breakfast.
What about the other
times you got sick?
- Home, I think.
- Your brother stop by then too?
Yeah. He feels awful.
I give him shit for being
such a terrible cook.
That was Aceveda. You're on your own.
What's up?
Thinking of transferring
off the team.
Why?
Not as much fun as I thought it'd be.
I'm not fitting in the
way that I wanted.
You're wanted.
- We're a tight bunch.
- There's no hard feelings.
You're cool, but...
Shane.
Look, I need to be somewhere
where I can be the go-to guy.
Detective?
Just sit tight, okay? I got
plans for you. Trust me.
Aceveda and Detective
Wyms need to see you.
Victim's Karen Rivas,
the homeless advocate.
She and her child were apparently
carjacked after a robbery.
Fortunately, the baby's fine.
The owner and his son. That's three
dead, including a public figure.
This is Claudette's case. Both
teams will take her lead.
Why both? We've knocked down
cases like this before.
- So have they.
- Don't worry, Mac man.
- You can back us up at the arrest.
- We huddle in five.
Get your marching orders.
Random crime. No video.
Media attention.
Lucky we're here.
Look, the boss ma'am's waiting.
What do you say we put
down a few notes on this?
First team to bring
in the shooter wins.
Who needs money?
Why don't we put up something that
really counts, like your pride?
All right, you guys lose,
Sasquatch has to take a bath.
Better yet, how about this?
The losing team streaks
through the Barn.
- Very 1 974 of you.
- You okay with that, daddy?
What sort of bet is that?
Put some money up.
- Yeah, be a man.
- Yeah.
Well, a real man puts his
dignity on the line.
Afraid your boys will fall short?
You guys have ladies. I gotta be
a gentleman, offer you an out.
Only ladies I see are you pussies
afraid to take this bet.
All right. You're on.
- And yours are gonna be off.
- Yeah, we'll see.
Rivas was driving a 1 999
white Mercedes S420.
Vic, put your guys on finding it.
Get the license plate and VlN number.
Put out an APB.
- Got it.
- Unis combed the crowd.
Of course, no one seems
to have seen anything.
- Walon, you find somebody who has.
- Annie, hit this crowd up again.
Trish, across the street. Eddie,
hit the neighboring stores.
Two cases inside were cleared out.
The shooter was looking
for something.
He couldn't get the register, took
something so it wasn't a bust.
Check if something's missing.
Ronnie, play bookworm.
I know a fence who'll buy anything.
Maybe the stuff will end up there.
Find out what's missing, take Shane.
Better yet, I'll start
hitting the fences.
- Call with the info.
- I'll come.
Let us know?
Good luck.
If the killer dumped the
car, it'll turn up.
Since he didn't get the
till, maybe he flipped it.
Let's hit the chop shops.
- Good. Report anything to me.
- Okay.
Already got a witness.
It was horrible.
I heard shots,...
...and then I saw this white guy
and this black girl run out...
...and they jacked this
lady's car, shot her dead...
...and threw her baby to the curb.
And all I could do was scream
for somebody to call 911.
How come you didn't report
what you saw immediately?
I went home to change,
put some makeup on.
- Why?
- I saw all the cameras.
I need the tape.
I been out here for six months. You
can't land a gig without tape.
- You're an actress?
- You have any idea how tough it is?
Aren't you worried the killers
know you can identify them?
- They don't know my name.
- It's on the news, right?
- But they won't know where I live.
- Are you in the phone book?
Y'all are gonna protect me, right?
- Edixon?
- All right.
Ronnie says the Decoy Squad
brought in some other witnesses.
Aceveda's definitely auditioning
them to replace us.
- Yeah, won't let it happen.
- Yeah, damn straight. Edixon. Hey.
Edixon!
Hey, it's getting harder to find you.
Took me all of two phone calls
today to track you down.
No.
- No Mercedes?
- No, no Mercedes.
Not another chop shop, Edixon.
Who's stealing for you?
Evil churro vendor?
- Now.
- Now!
Hey.
- lf I find Mercedes, I call, okay?
- Not good enough.
You're gonna tell everyone that you're
looking to buy. Pay top dollar.
- Yo.
- Tavon, yo.
- This is my partner, Shane.
- What up?
Listen, we're looking
for some things.
They were taken from
Ling's over on 5th.
Saw it on the news.
Can't say I'm sorry.
Those rat slants
always did outbid me.
Still, that's a rough way
to go out of business.
- Haven't seen any of it.
- You sure?
If you shelled out cash,
you wouldn't wanna say.
Yeah, I'm sure.
What you doing back there?
Like my partner says, just looking
for a little stolen bling-bling.
- Stuff involving a triple murder.
- And I don't have it.
Yeah, what do you have?
- Yo, man, what's up with partner boy?
- Hey, Shane, Meaty's cool.
If he says it ain't here, it ain't.
- Shit.
- Got a license to sell these?
Serial numbers filed off.
There's four in the box.
Look, asshole. I said I
didn't see your shit.
Now, leave mine alone.
Yeah? You're under arrest.
Turn around, skinny, let's go.
Hey, Shane. Come on,
what are you doing?
- Being an asshole.
- Come on, if it turns up, he'll call.
- Not anymore.
- See?
You gonna stand there? Can I
get a little help, please?
Your cuffs, man. One pair just
isn't doing it for this cat.
Don't worry. There's thousands more.
Can we finish this later? My
15 minutes are ticking away.
- Sit down.
- The truth is, I saw the sister good.
But the white guy with
her, they all sort of...
It's hard to differentiate.
Know what I'm saying?
Keep looking.
City just posted a $5000 reward.
Reward?
We got a few chop shops paying
top dollar for '99 Benzes.
If our shooters dump
it, my CLs will call.
What about the missing pawn items?
Ronnie went through the vic's ledger.
Turns out, all the missing items
were jewelry pawned by the same guy:
Dean Warrison.
Maybe he came back for his stuff.
We went by his place,
he moved months ago.
Talking to associates to
track down his new crib.
Trying to figure out who the
Bonnie is to his Clyde.
Robbery, breaking and
entering, drug possession.
Is that the man?
He's white. Could be.
Feels good. I'm gonna release...
...the make and model of
the car to the press.
Let them know we have two suspects.
How's the Decoy Squad doing?
Rivas' Amex card was used about
an hour ago at a gas station.
Walon's talking to the
station clerk now.
Kevin, someone's trying
to kill your brother.
We found traces of a deadly poison,
thallium, in Robert's stomach.
That doesn't sound right.
Especially since this is...
...the third time this month
he's been hospitalized for it.
You think he's trying
to kill himself?
That's an interesting theory.
Let's think it through.
Robert's got a decent job.
He's been there 12 years.
He owns his house. Seems
to have a lot of friends.
- No trouble dating. Healthy.
- Besides the food poisoning.
Besides the food poisoning.
So why would a guy like
that try to kill himself?
Depression?
Let's consider my theory.
You're unemployed, been to rehab.
You're broke.
You really don't have a lot going on.
But Robert made you his
insurance beneficiary.
Then he suffers a
rash of poisonings...
...all after you come over
to cook food for him.
A guy can't cook his
brother breakfast?
Look at the facts, Kevin.
You cook, he gets poisoned.
It's a little perspicuous,
don't you think?
You don't know what
"perspicuous" means, do you?
You think you're smart
enough to lie to me?
enough to convince me...
...you had nothing to do with this?
"Perspicuous" means obvious.
Well, it's obvious you're a xxxx.
Talked to one of Dean
Warrison's drug buddies.
Hasn't seen him, heard he moved
in with some black girl.
- Our Bonnie. What's the address?
- Still working on it.
Well, work harder.
Our killer's running around out there.
I don't wanna be running buck-naked.
Well, I got nothing to
be embarrassed about.
If I'd known, I'd have waxed my back.
I seen you in the shower. It's not
your back you need to worry about.
We gotta ID the girl.
His jacket said he was in rehab.
Run that down.
- Maybe they met there.
- All right.
I've been fielding calls from
chop shops. Nothing so far.
Take the mug shot
around to local motels.
- See if he's holed up somewhere.
- Good idea.
- Whose mug shot?
- Nobody.
- That's cold.
- Not as cold as you're gonna be.
I'm gonna crank up the a.c. in the
clubhouse so your sac shrinks.
I'll shrink your sac.
Detective, you know Carlos.
Daily News.
Carlos is gonna cover
our investigation...
...for a piece in the
Sunday magazine.
He's to have unlimited access.
- How did you get that assignment?
- It was your captain's idea.
Sir, chief of police is on the phone.
Tell him I'll call back.
Have a seat.
We'll get you started in a minute.
- I know you like the limelight...
- It's not about me.
A good Samaritan gets killed
while running errands?
It feeds into everyone's bad
perceptions about Farmington.
How's this piece gonna read if
this case doesn't get solved?
We have a suspect. We're
gonna solve this.
It's never a slam-dunk.
You said you have everything
you need to crack this.
So let's turn this press
coverage into a positive.
See about getting you
three square meals.
- Vic.
- What's up?
Shane arrested my Cl. He ruined
a five-year relationship.
- He's making me look like a punk.
- All right.
- What's going on?
- Caught Fatboy Slim here...
...filing serial numbers
off a few handguns.
What's this have to
do with our homicide?
Nothing. He's got his
head up his ass.
And I told him, back off.
Hey, you don't tell me anything.
I tell you.
When Vic's not around,
I am in charge.
My lead. My guy.
You believe this?
- Kick him.
- Kick him?
Look, I don't have time
for this bullshit.
We're trying to catch a killer
before the Decoy Squad does.
- Sorry, brother.
- No need. You ain't the bitch.
Hey, I just did you a favor.
Open your mouth one more time,
you'll be begging me to lock you up.
Now get out. Get out. Take your shit.
What was that about?
Passionate people having
a difference of opinion.
Trust me, it works.
Can I speak to you?
Guess I'll take advantage
of that unlimited access.
I went a little too far with the
poisoning victim's brother.
How'd you do that?
You were here with your photo shoot
and I was up there by myself.
So it's my fault?
I was trying something new.
Trying to... You know, a
curveball to my fastball.
Don't tell me you played bad cop.
- You weren't up there to stop me.
- I knew you could handle this.
Ninety percent of the time, yes.
But 10 percent, there's
a connection. We...
- It's like you...
- Please don't say I complete you.
Go up there and give
it one more shot.
You will go to a doctor,
get checked out.
I spend thousands of dollars...
Are you coming?
Yeah.
It's Julien's house.
We got a call about a disturbance.
Can we come in?
Sure.
Hey, Julien.
- Maybe we should go?
- No. No, it's okay.
It was just verbal.
I didn't realize it
had gotten that loud.
Actually, the call came
from this address.
What?
Randall.
Randall?
Did you call 911, honey?
Baby, I'm sorry. We
didn't mean to scare you.
Mind if I speak to the boy, ma'am?
- Go ahead.
- I'm gonna have to talk to Vanessa.
- Everything okay?
- Yes.
Are you feeling threatened or unsafe?
Lord, no. No.
Look, everything is fine.
He has been through so
much and it's hard on him.
The shame, the stress.
The surgery just...
- Surgery?
- For his back.
After the beating. He's already
had one and it still hurts him.
He might need another one.
I didn't know.
Randall just got scared, that's all.
We're all right.
The Decoy Squad got a call from
a motel clerk who saw the car.
- They're talking with him now.
- I got one better.
Got an ID on Dean Warrison's
roommate, the black female.
Her name is Danielle Riggs.
- You show the picture to the witness?
- ID'd her as one of the carjackers.
- Nice work.
- Thanks. More to do.
What was that before?
Tavon and Shane.
It's just two dogs humping.
If you can't pry them loose,
I can get my hose out.
I can handle it.
The Decoy Squad is working very well.
I don't want any worries
with your team.
You know they ain't in there.
I saw them both leave
early this morning.
Check it out.
Is this Danielle?
Is that her?
Yeah, that's her. She
left with the white boy.
- Damn it.
- All clear.
Here you go.
Robert's gonna stay in the hospital
overnight. Just for observation.
It's nothing to worry about.
So...
Listen.
I spoke to him again.
He...
He really cares about you.
Practically threw me
out of his room...
...when he found out we
were talking to you.
I can see there's a real bond there.
He says you've really
been trying hard lately.
- Is that what he said?
- Yeah.
You've blown a few
opportunities in the past...
...he's needed to bail you out.
Says it's added up to 1
5 grand over the years.
It's only 14.
The other investors hadn't gotten cold
feet and pulled out, then, you know...
You're one of these guys...
...who, it doesn't work out,
you just blame someone else?
And you're one of these guys
who's always just a xxxx.
I saw you and Lucas responded
to a domestic at Julien's.
- How did you know about that?
- New policy.
Any 91  call at an officer's
home address is flagged.
Everything all right?
Yeah, it was nothing.
Then why didn't you
put it in the report?
I brought you back to
be straight with me.
I thought our deal was
if I saw anything.
All I saw was a
husband-wife argument...
...and a kid who got
scared and called 911.
No special treatment.
There's a complaint against
Julien for excessive force.
Now this.
- Should I be worried for him?
- I'll talk to him. I'll let you know.
Lem and Tavon are sitting
on the apartment.
Shane and Ronnie are running
down the girl's family.
If they're still in town,
we're gonna nail them.
- You won't have to look far.
- We got him.
Interrogation 1.
- You brought in our guy?
- Looks that way.
How'd you find him?
Claudette gave us his sheet,
saw the drug-possession bust.
We followed up, discovered a
treatment program he attended.
We sat on a few methadone
clinics and bingo.
- You busted him based on my tip.
- Yeah.
Speaking of tips, give us a
little preview. Cut or uncut?
Heard about the shooting
at the pawnshop, Dean?
Not really, no.
Three people dead, shooter
runs out with jewellery.
Chains, rings, bracelets.
All stuff you hocked.
Just put him at the scene already.
Got a witness who saw you
run out of the store.
- I wasn't there.
- Sure, you were.
You and Danielle.
I didn't go in that shop.
It was Danielle and
my friend Crazyhouse.
- Crazyhouse?
- Danielle's boyfriend.
Got out of prison a
couple months ago.
He shot those people. Not me.
Make me believe.
I drove them there, but
I stayed in the car.
- He's not the shooter.
- I believe him. Start stripping.
I've been staying with Danielle.
Haven't been hitting her, though.
I needed cash, so I hocked a few
things. She didn't miss them.
Get to it.
Crazyhouse starts asking about
the jewellery he gave her.
I fessed up. He freaked out.
Made me drive them to the shop.
I stayed in the car.
When I heard shots...
...I jumped, man.
Man, he must have jacked
that car after I split.
And I didn't know he
was gonna kill no one.
- He's not the shooter.
- Accomplice.
We said the shooter.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You've got the killer's name
and his girl. Find them.
You're welshing?
The bet was who'd find
the shooter first.
That guy's the driver.
Are you welshing?
Okay. Bet's still on.
Yeah.
Got a little tip about the
missing car. See you.
It's half now, half later.
That's always been our deal.
Police. Hands up. Up.
Looking for someone?
Hear you're looking
to ditch a '99 Benz.
Sorry, can't help you. Right, Eddie?
Don't shoot. Who are you?
God. Cut the crap. You set me up.
- You're making an awful mistake.
- I don't think so.
I know who you are.
Long-lost friend.
Trying to dump off Rivas' car.
She might be able to
lead us to the shooters.
How come you never called?
Hey, Vic.
Thought you forgot my name.
- Welcome back.
- Yeah.
- How's it going?
- It's good.
I hear you're mentoring
Julien, sort of.
- What's going on?
- Nothing.
You looking out for him?
I just told Julien to
stand up for himself.
You mean like with Carlson
and his broken arm?
I don't know how
Carlson broke his arm.
I know no one's gonna
be giving Julien...
...another blanket
party anytime soon.
So I hear you're going
to the city council.
I just won the primary.
The general election
isn't for a few months.
Well, yeah, but you're
running unopposed, right?
Wait until all the votes are in before
making me the second Mrs. Aceveda.
Well, I'm sure the first Mrs. Aceveda
will have an objection or two.
Are your suspects usually so flirty?
No. Who are you?
...jacked that car you
were trying to sell.
They left three people dead.
Where are they?
I understand there's a reward.
For information leading
to their arrest.
I don't know where they are. I mean,
I just work for a car broker.
They called, said they were
looking to dump a '99 Benz.
I heard Edixon was buying.
I didn't know it was the ride you
were looking for till I was arrested.
So you never spoke to these people?
No.
But I can tell you where the car is.
I was careful. All that pristine
evidence, just sitting there.
And what will it cost me?
Just the reward.
Up front.
And my boss and I walk.
Hasn't talked to our shooters? She
knows more than she's saying.
We've gotta find that car.
I'm gonna give her immunity.
Kick her. Let me follow her.
See what she's playing.
The lead on the vehicle,
need us to run it?
Sure. Car thief just gave up the car.
Give me a sec. I'll give
you the exact location.
- Where have you been?
- Working a triple murder.
I can't get anywhere with the brother.
He hates me.
- Did you go through the house?
- No traces of thallium anywhere.
If he doesn't confess, he's gonna
walk out of here and do it again.
Robert totally trusts him. He can't
believe his brother poses any threat.
What do you want me to do?
Let's recapitulate. Your
brother is a success.
You are not.
Your brother has lots of money.
You're in the negative.
Your brother is a well-adjusted,
caring individual.
You...
...are fratricidal.
Which means, you're going to jail.
Is that perspicuous enough for you?
Perspicuous. You remember or
should I get a dictionary?
- What the hell's going on?
- I'm interrogating a suspect.
What is this shit?
Would you step outside?
Sorry. He's got an uncle
higher up on the force.
- We can't get rid of him.
- She's playing him.
I got here on merit.
I've been doing this job a
lot longer than he has.
And he's always trying
to teach me something.
Like I don't know what I'm doing.
Sorry.
I get worked up just
thinking about it.
- I get it.
- Yeah?
- I know someone like that.
- No offense...
...he can't possibly be this bad.
So, what are you gonna
do about Tavon?
Booting the black guy on the team...
...isn't gonna win us any favors
with a Hispanic captain...
...a black chief or a black nanny.
Besides, we need him.
- For what?
- He's an outsider.
He keeps us sharp about
the Money Train.
Bullshit. We never needed him before.
It's my call. Live with it.
All right, now this could be it.
Man, she's fast.
- All right, move in, boys. Move in.
- Copy that.
- Get out. Hands up.
- Get out!
Hands up. Get over here.
- Out of the car!
- Get out!
Against the car.
Man, twice in one day.
Damn. It's a good
thing we're friends.
- Is that your car?
- No, but I have immunity.
- No, not on this one, you don't.
- Vic.
You talked to the shooter.
Now, save the snow jobs for Aceveda
because I will press charges on this.
They sold us the stolen Mercedes.
They need a new car
to get out of town.
Hon, just let me handle this, okay?
We were gonna do the deal and then
we were gonna turn them in. I swear.
They were gonna pay
you for the wheels...
...and you were gonna get the reward.
Something like that.
I got a new plan.
Man, I hope these two
idiots don't blow it.
I'm worried about chucklehead. The
future Mrs. Aceveda'll do just fine.
Give me a second. Yeah?
Vic, Cassidy's missing.
- What?
- She's missing.
The sitter thought she
was in her room...
...but when I got home, she's gone.
- Did she run away?
- I think so.
Call the police.
They're on their way over.
I'll be right there.
Cassidy's missing.
- What do we do?
- Just get these guys.
Hey, wait a second, man.
Who's in charge?
We're a team. Just get it done.
Any word?
I've called her friends.
No one's seen her.
- Set a perimeter?
- We have six units on it.
Juvenile detectives
have been notified.
They'll set up a command center.
Good. Okay.
Her bike's missing.
Good. Probably means
she left on her own.
- Where would she go?
- I don't know.
- Think.
- I'm thinking.
- Were you here?
- Yes.
- Did you hear anything?
- No.
- Nothing?
- What were you doing?
- Vic.
I was working with Matthew.
Let's go find her.
What are you doing here?
Aceveda called in extra units until
those killers are in custody.
Hey, Julien. You think maybe
you came back too early?
What?
Maybe you should've stayed
on disability some more.
Vanessa worries too much.
Look, things are good for me now.
Better than they've ever been.
Here. At home.
I was at your home.
Come on, Julien. You're not yourself.
I am.
Yeah? Well, what happened
to Carlson then?
He got hurt.
Yo, Ronnie, that's them.
Gun!
Shit. He blew it.
- Get out of the way!
- Everybody down!
We know she's your girlfriend.
Let her go.
- I'll still kill her.
- Okay.
You got a car, man. Just go. Go, man.
- Don't move.
- Get on your stomach.
Hands up! Palms up!
- Turn him around.
- I got him.
Get your ass up. Let's go.
Was she upset or something?
I told her she couldn't go to
Piper's sleepover. She lost it.
I told her we were gonna talk
about it after I got home.
I thought you were
taking night shifts.
This was OT.
And then this happens.
Camilla was there and
Owen was with Matthew.
I don't even know Owen. And...
And who the hell is Camilla?
- Jesus Christ...
- We're getting a divorce.
I need to work. This is not my fault.
Whose is it, then?
Vic, shut up. Just shut up.
I didn't do it.
- What is it?
- It's a...
...quadrophenia report.
Positive traces of thallium
were found in your kitchen.
I didn't have any
thallium in my kitchen.
Then how do you explain that?
Okay, what...? What happens now?
Dutch gets his name in the papers.
Egomaniac roped in a reporter
to do a story on him.
He's in the building.
So everybody'll know he busted me?
He was assigned the case.
He gets credit.
Well...
What if I tell you what happened?
I guess that I'd get the credit.
Well, it's not like you think.
I mean, I knew I could never pay
Robert back all that money.
And the thallium, it just...
It just seemed easier than
disappointing him again.
- There.
- Stop.
Cass. Are you okay?
Yep.
Cass?
All right, come on, let's go.
Cassidy.
Let's go.
Right now.
I decided to partner you up again.
I thought Tommy and l were
doing well together, sir.
You two have a history.
This made more sense.
Do you have a problem with this?
Not if Julien doesn't.
Trust me, this will work.
You'll start riding
together tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
How's Cass, man?
She's good.
Looks like you guys did
just fine without me.
- Yeah.
- That's right.
Lookie what we got.
Now you can get the
chief on the phone.
The shooter's in custody?
It's chilly in here.
Somebody turn up the
air conditioning?
- How'd you find them?
- By running my ass off.
Wyms had us going over the stolen
car looking for nose hairs.
So how about a preview?
Bikini or Brazilian?
- Hey.
It's good stuff out there today.
Avoided a shootout at the swap meet.
Could have got real ugly.
- It was no biggie.
- Yes, it was.
It was great work.
You don't have to go overboard.
I do when I'm about to
ask someone a big favor.
I need you to work it out with Shane.
- Tell him.
- You could be the bigger man here.
I dig what you do. And Shane...
- He's a cracker with 'tude.
- He's acting out because you're good.
Help me make him feel secure.
- Send him to a shrink.
- I'm gonna talk to him too.
But I'm asking you, take one
for the team here. For me.
Shit.
Babe, what are we doing?
Maybe it's God's plan for
us just to have Randall.
I want my own child too. With you.
Randall is your child.
A man like Shane Vendrell...
...can get his woman pregnant
without even trying.
We're trying. We'll just...
We'll keep trying.
You know what I mean.
You're not comfortable. I don't
want another fight about this.
No fight.
I will go to the doctor and
I will see what I can do.
Two cases in one day.
You're on a roll.
You're the one who
solved the poisoning.
I was just your pawn.
That's one way of
looking at it, I guess.
So, what's your story?
You running your two teams...
...or are you still a
measly detective with me?
I'm whatever you need me to be.
And what if I need
you to complete me?
Please don't say that.
Hey.
What's going on?
A baby, man. Congratulations.
I can't feel anything.
Looks like you're feeling something.
Look, man, I was
hoping we could talk.
Yeah, what about?
Figured we could work some shit out.
How you feeling?
As long as I have ginger ale
and crackers, I'm fine.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
So you want anything?
Just to clear the air.
I'm gonna go check on the laundry.
Bye.
- Okay.
All right, look. The Strike
Team, that's your gig, okay?
You and Vic, you established
it, everyone knows that.
I just wanna add what
I can to the mix.
I appreciate that.
But I don't wanna be along for
the ride if I'm not wanted.
I wasn't trying to be a dick.
Me and Vic built this thing...
...and I don't want somebody
coming in and screwing it up.
I won't.
You coming here and
apologizing, I get that.
As long as you know your
place, we'll be all right.
My place?
What, like back of the bus?
What, you think you're
driving the bus?
You know what? He doesn't
wanna hurt your feelings...
...but Vic has plans for me.
He's my best friend.
He's been my best
friend for seven years.
You think he's gonna push
me aside for some darkie?
Get off!
Stop it!
- Where you going?
- No.
- No!
- Where you going?
- Come here.
- No!
- Come here! Come here!
- Stop!
Let go of me! Let go of me!
Let go of me!
- No.
- Let go of me!
Please.
My God.
I wanted you to know. That
little problem before?
- All taken care of.
- Good.
My guys did good today.
Just as long as they
keep their clothes on.
You heard about that?
Little wager. Good
incentive for a great job.
Lucky you didn't lose.
- I wasn't worried.
- No, lucky for us you didn't lose.
Call 911, man. Somebody.
Gentlemen, this way, please.
Let's go. Keep moving.
Cage is clear. Give them
the two-minute warning.
- Hello?
- I spoke to Cassidy's teacher.
You know, the usual "this is normal
in a divorce" kind of stuff.
- Well, what do we do now?
- We all need to sit down together...
- ...and work it out with a counselor.
- Listen.
This wasn't your fault.
I was just...
I was out of my mind.
- I know.
- Okay.
I'm just glad she's home.
- Me too.
- Okay.
God.
I cannot believe that Shane
and Tavon just missed that.