Previously on "The Shield".
Just because you been
on the sidelines...
...doesn't mean you have
to play Wonder Woman.
Though I might be able to
dig up the outfit for you.
Victim's name is Isabel
Nelson, raped by a lone male.
Guy was waiting in the house
naked when she came home.
Isabel's 73.
We think this cuddler rapist
has been around for a while.
Mueller's results have been proven
accurate down to the square block.
His fee is $5000.
- Right.
- No. We don't have the money.
Two of the bills you had in
your possession were marked.
Currency stolen from an
Armenian money-laundering ring.
Holy shit.
We've been waiting for it to show up.
- Guess what?
- Our money is marked?
It showed up in your hands.
Chew on this, baby.
We just found out the feds marked
some of our money train cash.
- What?
- Part of a sting they're doing...
- ...on the Armenians.
- Shit.
Deep.
I get this to the lab before 5...
...I can get fingerprint results
by morning. You coming?
I'm curious what else
we might find here.
Police! On your knees, man.
Let's see that mouth. Suck it!
Anything?
Shit.
All right, we switch, do it
all again with new eyes.
- Goddamn.
- Shit.
We can't spend a nickel until
we know which bills are marked.
I'm gonna check for dummy
serial numbers this time.
Who's got the Federal Reserve seal?
I'll take it. Here.
The cuddler rape case.
- How many victims so far?
- Five.
- We're going to the press tomorrow.
- No. Not yet.
The reporters are already calling.
They've got the story.
We'll give them our side.
We got a list of sex offenders,
guys with prior robberies.
Let us talk to them first.
There've gotta be a hundred suspects
at least. It'll take you a month.
Actually, we've narrowed
the list down to 1 4.
How?
- We got the geo-profile.
- I said no to that.
When I told the profiler
who the victims were...
...he offered to do
it for half-price.
His grandma put him through school.
It's still too much.
Twenty-five hundred.
I wrote him a check.
If it doesn't work out,
take it out of my salary.
Believe me, I will.
Okay.
The profiler gave us hot zones, places
where the guy likely lives or works.
Plus we've got high-risk
areas for future rapes.
Talk to whoever you need to.
But you got 24 hours till
the press conference.
What if our guy has a lust for fame?
Going public will build his
confidence, make him more dangerous.
Give us another week.
Potential rape victims
need to know the threat...
...and they need to know it now.
You've got until tomorrow.
You're early.
You wanted me to check
the pool filter.
I'll do it before I
take Cass to the game.
Okay, I'll go get her ready.
- Noisy.
- Right.
Hey, Mr. Mackey. How's it going?
- Hey, little man.
- That's enough for today, Matthew.
You did a good job. I'm proud of you.
Let's pack up.
He's working on understanding
concepts as well as objects.
Like a horn's not just
a horn, but it's...
Noisy. I get it. It's good.
Matthew, those don't go there.
Let's put them in your
room right now, okay?
- He can get it later.
- He knows he needs to do it now.
And I said he can do it later.
I got a job for him.
She's getting her uniform on.
She'll be out in a minute.
I'll be by the pool. Come on, Matt.
Help your dad.
Hey, I talked to a nurse.
Tavon's doing a lot better.
- That's great.
- Yeah. Yeah, it is.
- He's off the ventilator.
- Who? Tavon?
Yeah. He's still not
responding to voices...
...but breathing on his
own was a big hurdle.
He could have a full recovery.
I'm gonna see him after work.
- Anybody wanna come with?
- I can't make it today.
Look, I got another idea on
how to track those bills.
You know those lists the feds send
around to banks to track counterfeits?
You can't just walk into a bank...
...and ask to see their watch list
without attracting attention.
Those lists also go around to
check-cashing places, lndian casinos.
Anyway, I know this wink
joint, he cashes checks.
I go in, I tin Uncle Ho, say I need
to make sure his list is current.
He'll go for that?
If it keeps me from poking around his
backroom where he's pimping cooch.
Yeah, I think he'll go for it.
Yeah, that's not bad.
- Just keep it quiet.
- Okay.
All here.
You're assigned to Trish for the day.
I'll try to break you in easy.
Got gay bashers going after male
hustlers out on the stroll.
Where's the rest of the Decoy Squad?
- Deep cover.
- Trish will fill you in...
- ...on operational details.
- Just for the record.
I have no problem working
with the Decoy Squad...
- ...but we don't work for them.
- That's right. You work for me.
- Who the hell wrote this?
- Who do you think? Nina.
What, are we in third grade?
Hey, that yours?
- Tommy Hisk?
- Yeah?
Detective Kouf, Wilshire.
Can I talk with you?
- Shoot.
- Do you wanna come with me?
I'm about to go on duty.
Just step outside.
Go get the captain.
Your ex-wife and son
were found murdered.
I'm very sorry.
I need to take you
to Wilshire with me.
- Wait a minute. Why?
- That's my captain's orders.
This happens, he wants to sweat him?
- Just a couple of questions.
- We're all cops here.
Think I had something
to do with this?
It's procedure. What do you want?
Save him the car ride, and
you talk to him here.
You do it fast, and
you get it over with.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
Where were you last night
between 10 and 11 p.m.?
- Is that when they...?
- Just where were you?
I don't know. I worked
late and went home.
Okay. Were you with anyone
like a girlfriend maybe or...?
- I don't have a girlfriend.
- I'm sorry?
I don't have a girlfriend.
This is bullshit.
I heard his divorce got
nasty, but come on.
They'll get a statement,
see there's nothing there.
Meanwhile, the real killer's
trail is going cold.
It's Wilshire's case.
Your team's got yours.
- How old was his kid?
- Four or 5. Goddamn it.
We gotta posse up.
Find out who did Tommy's family.
Who's coming?
True they got him up
in Interrogation?
We're gonna fix that.
Talking about disappearing
off the grid?
If the hammer doesn't come
down fast and hard...
...the message is cops and
their families are fair game.
I got cage duty. What
can I do from here?
Run a records search.
Anyone Tommy's put away,
recently paroled.
I'll check out the crime scene.
You canvas the neighborhood.
Okay.
Change of plans. I'm calling in sick.
Are you?
I could put a penny under my tongue
or you can take me at my word.
This about that family
getting killed?
The only reason your boss
is dicking with Tommy...
...is because Aceveda took you
and your team from Wilshire.
This is payback.
What am I supposed to tell Claudette?
Tell her I was present
and accounted for.
She spanks me, I'll spank you.
- Hey, Vic. I'm coming too.
- No.
I'm not sitting around on flamer
duty while Tommy gets boned.
You've got problems of your own if
Tavon comes to. I need you here.
- Vic, come on.
- I got some bodies.
I'll handle it. You
handle this for me.
Hey, Julien. You hear about Tommy?
Yeah. No way he did this.
A bunch of us are going out
there to prove it. You want in?
Yeah. He was my partner,
I knew his son.
It's a deep blue run. There could be
consequences, a little hot water.
- Okay.
- Good, you're in. Let's go.
Did you place any calls, so
we can prove you were home?
No. Look, I wanna see them.
When can I see them?
It's all right. We won't
be here too long.
Excuse me a minute.
She's been crying for you.
She doesn't understand
where you've been.
I'm sorry, it's been
really busy right now.
You're always busy.
That's never stopped you
from coming home before.
- I can't get into it right now.
- Well, we're here right now.
That's all you gotta say?
- Will you be home for dinner?
- I don't know how long I'll be.
- Spending the night?
- I don't know.
For God's sake, what
have you been doing?
One of my cops found out his
family's been murdered.
On top of that, he's a suspect. And
then you've been calling all day.
Then you bring Sophia down here.
You know, what are you thinking?
You know, qué piensas?
Calm down.
Yeah.
Hey.
I'll be home when I get home.
I'll call it in.
Mind if we take a look around?
You're in the wrong
district, aren't you?
This was the family
of one of our guys.
Yeah. I heard.
Techs are still inside.
No one's gonna disturb
your crime scene, man.
Normally, sure, but the captain's
taken a special interest in this.
He could stop by any time.
We just wanna help out a friend
who lost his wife and kid.
He was caught up in the
middle of a pissing match...
...between your boss and ours.
Look, I'm not trying to
be a pain in the ass.
Two minutes. We just
wanna see what happened.
Look, they can wait outside.
Just me and Tommy's partner.
- Two minutes. In and out.
- Thanks.
He came in a back window.
Broken lock.
Wife was stabbed a couple dozen times.
The sister found her.
Anything missing?
Off the top of her head, a silver
tea set and some jewellery.
The kid ran to hide under the bed.
Killer found him and
slashed his throat.
You think God's gonna show any
mercy to the person who did this?
How bad was it?
That was a speed murder. The guy
had to be cranked on something.
Neighbors say there's been
a lot of break-ins lately.
There's a crack house right
over there, across the street.
Hey, anybody check that
rock house over there?
We knocked. No answer.
For Christ's sake.
Hey, Vic, wait a minute. I
just got my job back, okay?
I'm not breaking into this place.
There's a citizen inside here in
need of immediate medical attention.
See? Medical emergency. Somebody
get this man an aspirin.
Rise and shine, party people.
Yo, dude, this is my crib.
A cop's wife and kid across the
street were murdered last night.
This looks like a good place to
round up the usual suspects.
Ain't nobody here last
night except myself.
Well, that makes you a prime suspect.
Y'all tripping for real.
I was too blind off a eight ball to
raise my hand against my fellow man.
Are you playing a game with me?
Because I know some games myself.
Come on, Vic.
Okay.
This slanger, Darontay, came by
here last night to make a delivery.
He sees that bitch outside writing
down his goddamn license plate.
Darontay goes out to regulate.
Tells her to get ghost or
be swarmed on by a nigga.
- What happened then?
- I don't know, man.
When homes came with the product...
...I was too busy trying
to get my smoke on.
If Tommy's wife wrote down this guy's
license, maybe it's inside the house.
Look, I think I saw some kind of
list on the fridge. I'm not sure.
Okay. Here's what we do.
I need another quick look inside.
I got a call that Captain
Griggs is on the move.
Come on, man, I'm just
trying to lend a hand here.
Then turn around and walk away.
I thought we were working
on the same team.
I don't know what this beef
between our captains is...
You want me to break it down for you?
No. I just want you out of
here before mine shows up.
All right, I'm out of here.
Plate numbers. I figure the
last one belongs to Darontay.
- Copy the last few to be safe.
- Gonna turn that over to Wilshire?
- After we run the numbers. Why?
- It's their investigation.
They're focusing on the wrong guy.
Wait a minute. Breaking and entering?
Withholding evidence?
If the perp fences the stuff
he stole before we get him...
...it'll be harder to tie him to
the case. We gotta get him now.
I signed to keep Tommy out
of jail, not put myself in.
Please. We're just doing the
job they should be doing.
- Julien, come on, let's go.
- I'm gonna see this through.
We're on patrol.
It's not like I haven't
covered for you...
...for a couple of hours when
you've had an emergency.
- You got the numbers?
- Yeah.
Feel free to return
the list to Wilshire.
There was another
break-in last month.
- She tell you about that?
- She told me.
Same as last night.
Came in through the same window,
stole a bunch of valuables.
- Luckily no one was home at the time.
- Why not look for a break-in guy?
Not a very good neighborhood for a mom
and kid to be living alone, is it?
It's shit. I tried to get Barb to
move, but she likes the house.
I don't make enough cash
for something better.
You fought?
So they argued. She's an ex-wife.
Comes with the territory.
Divorce was final two
weeks ago, right?
What's that to do with anything?
Like you said,...
...it's tough to get a house in
the Hills on a uniform's alimony.
Why the hell is that important?
- We're here to discuss last night.
- Am I interrogating you or him?
I thought we were just talking.
I reconned three victims'
homes last night...
...all with windows
facing the street.
Tried to get a look inside.
Drapes were closed in
all three instances.
- I can't wait to hear the punch line.
- I reinterviewed the victims.
Before the attacks, all had their
drapes up during the day...
...but closed at night. So?
He's scoping them out during the day.
Unemployed?
Be less conspicuous if
he worked in the area.
A courier, construction, someone
you wouldn't look at twice.
How's it going up there?
You guys any closer to a suspect
or are you just $2500 poorer?
We're gonna need daily surveillance
patrols in areas of potential attacks.
Save it till after the
press conference.
I've got my notes.
No, keep them. You're
gonna be doing it.
The press conference?
You always do those.
I gotta get back up to Tommy.
I still think this is premature.
We should release a psych profile,
see if it gets us any tips.
What's the profile?
Single, or with a
submissive partner...
...frees him up for
going out at all hours.
No. Enough of the profiles.
Just give them what we know.
I need you to run a plate.
One-zero-zero-Paul-Charles-Edward.
Should come back to an
owner, first name Darontay.
Yeah, I need an address ASAP.
Hey, I hit that check-cashing place.
Palmed the numbers
Treasury's watching.
Everything's under control here.
- What, you can't talk?
- Right.
Soon as we're done, me and the guys
will check our cash against that list.
We don't know if your Cl's
information is correct.
His info may not jive with
Aceveda's expectation.
Aceveda's working off
a different list?
Correct.
You need to review the evidence...
...collected in the Byz
Lats investigation.
Check it against the bills we
know are marked in Property.
There you go.
Hey, Cacuzza.
I could use a little help on
this Byz Lat investigation.
There was some cash logged into
Property, last name Salcido.
Can't release property without
the owner's signature.
Doesn't need to leave the room.
Drug residue on those bills gets
me the search warrant I need.
All right.
Here it is, the marked bills
we're holding for Treasury.
Great.
You haven't been back at
the house since you left?
Picked up Jeff a few
times outside the house.
That's the only reason,
to pick up Jeff?
- You heard him.
- Jesus Christ.
The thing is, one of the few items...
...that was stolen last
month in the break-in...
...was an American Eagle coin
collection from your father.
We talked to Barb's sister.
She said your son saw the coins
last week at your place.
He told his mom.
She said she was gonna
press charges...
...breaking and entering. That
would have cost you your job.
Tommy?
- Somebody made a mistake.
- Yeah? What's your son, a liar?
My son's dead, and you
pricks won't let me see him.
- Captain.
- Steve.
What's going on, David?
Why isn't he in custody?
Well, you said just a
few routine questions.
There is a case. I'm not obliged
to lay it out in front of him.
Why don't you lay it
out in front of me?
Okay. He breaks into
his ex-wife's house.
Stole property, she found out.
He kills her to cover it up.
The son sees it, so he kills him too.
Well, you've got nothing to support
that. So why don't you just let it go?
So if I search his place, I'm
not gonna find those coins?
Steve, you know you don't have
enough for a search warrant.
Are you still working with us...
...or are you a defence attorney now?
Cuff him, put him in the car.
No, he stays in my house
until you show me more.
Let's call the chief.
Sure. Yeah. I think he's on the
tenth hole at Rancho Park.
I'll make sure to tell him what...
...a great job the Decoy
Squad's doing for me.
Or you can finish up with Tommy here.
Next time, I won't knock so hard.
Put your clothes on, walk out the
door, and change your taste in men.
- Where were you last night, playboy?
- You know, ruling the streets.
Then back to the crib for a
little thug passion with shorty.
There was a double homicide...
...right down the block from
the crack house you supply.
Police officer's wife and
child were stabbed to death.
See me crying?
Well, we only just got here.
Did you do it?
I would have, but I
had on a new suit.
You wear that around your
neck and you talk like that?
You like the bling-bling.
Twenty-five grand.
Yo, why you tripping, nigga?
Two less blue-eyed
devils in this world.
Witnesses saw you arguing last night.
Who didn't have words with that bitch?
Telling folks to come correct...
...or get dimed on because
her baby daddy five-0.
Hell, even your boy couldn't deal.
Hired a straight G to
come gank his own crib.
No speak Ebonics, shithead.
Her old man hired some dude to
come rob his own damn house.
How do you know?
My users tell me
things of interest...
...Like when a fellow smoke hound
gets recruited by the po-po.
- Who'd this cop hire?
- Some smoker.
Probably wasn't a wise choice.
You hired someone to
knock over your house?
- No.
- Cut the bullshit, Tommy.
I found out.
Now, we got about two minutes tops.
Tell me what happened.
I have a coin collection from my dad.
Gold American Eagles.
She got half of them in the
settlement. She was gonna sell them.
So you hired someone
to steal them back?
It was a one-time thing.
Christ. You know, a bunch of us are
out there trying to clear your name.
You're making us all
look like assholes.
He was a 459 suspect I
cut loose who owed me.
Nothing to do with last night.
He came through the same
window, the same broken lock.
Ex-wives know how to push buttons.
One way of getting out
from under the alimony.
My son, Vic? You think I would
do this to him? You got kids.
Yeah. I wouldn't hire some crackhead
to break into where they sleep.
Barb and Jeff were out of town.
He wasn't a crackhead.
What, did you make him
take a urine test?
This guy came back for
seconds, killed them both.
Jesus Christ.
- I gotta find him.
- That's what I'm doing.
Tell me his name.
Hey, unlock this door.
Soren Arnovic. All right, run
his priors, you'll find him.
I didn't know, Vic. If he
did this, I didn't know.
Keep your mouth shut.
Let me do my thing.
I said unlock this door.
What's going on?
Just showing a fellow
officer some support.
The rapes appear to be
preferentially-motivated assaults.
Can you put that in terms
our viewers can understand?
Yes. Women, between the ages...
...of 65 and 80, living alone.
The perpetrator, rapist...
...watches for women to leave the
house, enters, and waits for them.
If you live in the area, keep
your blinds drawn at all times...
...because he scopes out his
victims during the day.
We believe he's a white or
Latino male, aged 25 to 40.
That's three-quarters
of the population.
You don't have any hard suspects?
We're making progress
with our investigation.
Sounds like you have nothing.
We know he thinks of himself
as a sophisticated predator.
But really he has low intelligence
and poor interpersonal skills.
Probably in a menial
job or unemployed.
It's doubtful that he has a woman.
If he does, he's domineering and
can come and go as he pleases.
And he struggles with impotence.
Thank you, that's all.
- One more question, detective.
- I'm sorry. No.
Impotence?
I said he struggles with impotence.
He never ejaculates.
- Dutch.
- It's a solid tactic.
Emasculate him in public, you draw
him out or you defuse his impulses.
Or piss him off. What if he uses
this as an excuse to rape again?
He's raped five women
that we know of.
He doesn't need an excuse.
Ran those bills from Evidence. They're
not showing up on the Treasury list.
Aceveda's working off
a different list?
The question is how to flush it.
- Hey.
- I got an address.
All right. Meet back here after
you're done. We'll get into it.
Hear Tommy might not be as
clean as we'd like to think.
Think what you want to.
We gotta get back on patrol.
What would you say if it was
you in lnterrogation...
- ...for two murders you didn't do?
- Look, I'm not taking another fall.
You guys go back out there,
I gotta go to Aceveda.
Let's go.
Tell us about the coins.
I got guys at your
apartment right now.
They gonna find them?
According to the divorce settlement,
they belonged to Barb, right, Tommy?
- Part of the division of property?
- I wanna see my lawyer.
You helping us or trying
to hide something?
Did you have anything
to do with the robbery?
Let me see my son or get me a lawyer.
A lawyer? Not a PBA rep?
You can take him.
Let's go, buddy. Stand up.
Three assaults on gay hustlers in the
last month, all on Saturday nights.
- Victims give us anything?
- Besides big sad eyes?
Descriptions are all over the
place, but the M.O. tracks.
Four to five guys
grabbing for trick money.
We're shutting down Vice
in Farmington, right?
- That's the job.
- So if I'm a cocksucker...
What do you mean "if"?
...and shit goes down in my place...
...don't I just take my
mouth someplace else?
You may find it trivial...
...but two victims ended up in
ICU, one with a fractured skull.
Shane, you'll be undercover.
Everyone else maintains a perimeter.
Hold the phone there, doll face.
You got me on salami patrol? No.
- What about one of these guys?
- They don't look gay enough.
Shane, when you want
your buddy to release...
...gently squeeze the
shaft at the base...
...applying tongue to
the glans and frenulum.
Hey, tube-steak...
...I'm engaged to a gorgeous
female who's carrying my child.
You're the one who actually
knows the names of xxxx parts.
You must be the undercover
police officer.
I'm glad to be of service.
- Thanks.
- For what?
For watching our backs. It's
been the mama of drama here.
You might wanna hold
off on the thanks.
More than likely, I'll be
running you in next week.
I didn't get your name.
Yeah.
I got a call. Guy claiming
to be the rapist.
He's demanding a formal statement
retracting the impotence charge.
So he's made contact.
We've had over 100 calls.
It could be a hoax.
Well, he said he took a figurine
from the last victim's house.
Could say you take a figurine
from an old woman's house...
...and have a nine out of
10 shot at being right.
He says it was a Hummel.
Danny's not gonna say anything.
She wouldn't do that to me.
She sure as hell isn't
gonna do it to you.
Listen, we find this guy, after what
he did, we don't take any chances.
He resists, he reaches for a piece, he
lifts a finger, we use deadly force.
Not gonna give him a chance
to hurt us. Or Tommy.
- Sir?
- What is it?
Our deal was if I saw something...?
What happened?
Vic rounded up some guys to track
down who killed Tommy's family.
I was one of them. I mean,
just to make sure...
...Tommy was getting a fair shake.
- But now?
- But now...
...it's gone from a fact-checking
mission into a foxhunt.
- And who's with him?
- Julien.
- You let this happen?
- Well, I'm not his TO anymore, am l?
Obviously, Julien is
responsible for himself.
I thought you had some
influence over the guy.
Okay.
Six-Paul-1 1 requesting
backup at 95 Round Hill Road.
Possible 1 87 suspect.
All right, you take the front.
He sees the uniform,
he runs, he did it.
I'll take the back.
Hey, hey. No chances.
Police!
He's got a gun!
He's running! Police!
He's still got the gun.
Couldn't get a good shot.
Go out front, wait for backup.
Don't come near me.
When he calls, tell him the only way
the public's gonna hear his story...
...is for him to come
forward and tell the truth.
- What if he doesn't call?
- He's gonna wanna hear our answer.
You think he'll give it all up just
to make it clear he's not impotent?
- Why would he do that?
- Because he's mentally ill.
Don't come near me.
Thing I couldn't take
about prison, the stink.
Piss, shit....
You're looking at 10 years of that
before they hit you with the needle.
The worst part? Can't fix
up when you're hurting.
Sometimes you can't fix at all.
- Shut up.
- Me?
I'd eat a bullet right now.
Backup's two minutes out.
You got two minutes before
the cavalry gets here.
You think it over.
Suspect who killed Tommy Hisk's family. Saw
the stolen property in the house.
Vic's trying to get him to come out.
Hope he doesn't try too hard.
Stick the gun in your mouth and pull.
Last chance. Do it, Soren.
Don't shoot!
Please, don't shoot.
Put your hands behind your head.
Turn around.
Take him.
Come here.
Behind your back.
- Check out the wheels.
- Chrome 22s, sweet.
- How much do you think?
- I don't know.
Couple of night's work.
Set of Kruz Laguna chrome
22s, run you around 3200.
Throw in another grand
for the spinners.
Looks like our breeder knows a
thing or two about rim jobs.
Rim jobs.
In front of the camera, so the
cops can't do nothing to me.
I can arrange that.
I'll say what I gotta say, but
he's gotta take back what he said.
No one there except you, me and him.
-  You mean Detective Wagenbach?
- He needs to apologize.
I'm putting one of my
men in with the camera.
No, not unless you know someone
who can run a Sony D600.
You get the arrest, we get the video.
I've done this dozens of times.
My camera guy was in the middle of
Baghdad when Desert Storm started.
I want at least two guys
in close proximity.
I can handle him.
Three backup teams
with radio contact...
...and everyone's wearing a
vest or you get no video.
Back home, I had a Chevy 1500.
Four-barrel carb on a high-rise.
Slapped them paddle
tires on every summer.
Sand-dragged the shit out of it.
I had an F-1 50 with a NOS system...
...so the nitrous shot
straight into the manifold.
My brother did that
to a Dodge short bed.
- It's a bad move.
- No shit.
Threw a rod, sent it
sideways, tires smoked.
Junked the whole engine, Yeah.
- Hey, faggot.
- Hey, come here, punk.
Yeah, come on. Come on.
Move!
Police officer!
Drop the bat! Drop the bat right now!
Police. Stop right there.
Turn around.
- You, on the ground! On the ground!
- Turn around.
Turn around. Get over here.
Get over here. Against the wall.
This way. This way.
Stop right there!
Nice tackle.
What's this?
The collar you and me have
been working on all day.
Right. We're good.
DA says this case has got the
makings of a hate crime.
But they were also
in it for the money.
- Got a confession out of one.
- Spilled his guts.
Football players. They knock back a
few and look for queers to beat up.
Rip them off for their trick
money to pay the bar tab.
How'd the Strike Team do?
Fine. That one's a natural
born undercover come-guzzler.
I heard that, bitch.
You went off the grid today?
Who told you that?
I knew Tommy didn't do it.
Didn't like that Griggs asshole
trying to prove otherwise.
Today was a one-time thing. Got it?
Got it.
You weren't at the
basher sting tonight?
I was there in spirit.
Busts got made.
You never disappeared for a couple
of hours to help another cop?
You look like hell. Is
everything else all right?
Long day, that's all.
I replaced the gasket on the filter.
It's working just fine again.
Thanks for doing that.
- Matt having another session?
- Not tonight.
Owen's here a lot lately, isn't he?
Matthew's improving.
- Something you want to tell me?
- About what?
About you and Owen.
- Did Cassidy say something?
- No.
You walked by in your panties
without batting an eye...
...that he was just inside.
I don't have to discuss
this with you.
Yes, you do.
I want him the hell
away from Matthew.
- He's not his father.
- No, but he's here for him.
I'm not shelling out my own money...
...so that the hired help can
play daddy to impress you.
- Get rid of him.
- He's an amazing teacher...
...and that's what you pay for.
Anything else is my business.
You know he has a record?
- He got busted for weed in college.
- You've been checking up on him?
Damn straight. He's
alone with my son.
So he smoked a joint 15 years ago.
It wasn't possession.
It was for dealing.
It couldn't have been that serious
if he got his teaching certificate.
You date who you want,
but he's out of a job.
Talked to a buddy over at Wilshire.
Arnovic's given a full confession.
- Good.
- Not good.
He's telling about how Tommy...
...had him break into his
ex's house last month.
- What's that gonna mean for him?
- Probably his job.
I didn't have a shot.
I know.
Did the right thing riding with me
today. People saw you stepped up.
I'm going to church tonight.
I'll say a prayer for him.
For his wife and kid.
Say one for all of us.
It's now four hours past the
designated surrender time...
...of the alleged rapist
terrorizing elderly women...
...in the Farmington
District of Los Angeles.
Is he sending a message that it's
your department who is impotent?
You may as well turn this off,
because it's never gonna air.
We're chasing our tails.
We'd be better off if the
money train never happened.
- Give me a break.
- Calm down, girls.
Now, we know Treasury's got
Aceveda checking bills...
- ...on any bust over a grand.
- So?
One of the uni's just logged
two large into Evidence.
We don't let that money
out of our sight...
...we'll find the list
he's working with.
Here's your phone list and
your schedule for tomorrow.
- Did you call Aurora back?
- Not yet.
- You really should.
- I'll do it when I do it.
- What?
- Something's bothering you.
- lf it's anything that I did...
- It's not, Nina.
Please, just check the bills in
Evidence like I asked you to.
- What do you need?
- Shane forgot...
...to sign that evidence
envelope from that 211.
- No, he signed it.
- All right. Great. I'll let him know.
- He was never coming.
- No.
I embarrassed him, he
wanted to embarrass me.
Probably.
He's more self-controlled
than I gave him credit for.
We still got some time before
we have to get back to work.
- You could buy me breakfast.
- I'm broke.
We know where he
lives, where he hunts.
Now we've got him on tape.
Voice analysis will tell us his
ethnicity, personality traits.
We're getting to know him.
I was wrong.
You were right.
Maybe a little.
Come on.
I'm buying.
Hey, Nina. Could you help with the
computer in the briefing room?
It's not taking my access code.
- I can't right now.
- It's really kind of urgent.
I'm trying to access this database.
I'm working on something for David.
Sorry.
- Thank you.
- Have a good night.
Close it.
List's in Aceveda's safe.
- Well, so that's it.
- Not necessarily.
What do you mean?
Ripping off the money train was
10 times more complicated.
It's in a safe, in a captain's
office, inside of a police station.
Without that list, none of
that money is any good.
Yeah.
Gotta be a way.