Previously on "The Shield".
If there's a mole, it's not
Claudette's fault that you got made.
It is if she's submitting
wiretap requests for us.
I don't Trish back in one
piece, I'll use every favor...
...I've banked for the last 14
years to get your lazy ass fired.
She belongs behind a desk.
Not messing with what
we do on the street.
She's been playing both of us
against each other from the jump.
Now, if we start playing
ball together...
She can't command if
we don't let her.
Let's see that mouth. Suck it!
- And you couldn't stop them?
- He had a gun to my head.
Do you know who they are?
I could find out. But
even then, what?
If it was me, I'd kill them.
It's been really busy right now.
You're always busy.
That's never stopped you
from coming home before.
- What's going on?
- There's money missing.
- We're missing 7000.
- Including some marked money.
Ronnie reported the money missing.
Lem didn't even wanna steal
it in the first place.
- I didn't take that money.
- You think there's any chance...
- ...Vic took that money?
- Shut the hell up.
Who's gonna steal seven grand
and leave a fortune behind?
Wheelchair to Admitting.
I'm on. I'm on it.
- 5'7", short hair.
- Christ.
- Are you okay?
- You didn't have to come.
- What happened?
- I was patching up this Asian guy...
...and I saw he had a
gunshot wound to the arm.
When I went to call it
in, he freaked out.
Damn it.
You know, nothing's broken.
I'll be okay.
I got all the details.
- Any gang tats?
- No, just track marks.
He's either on something
or off his meds.
I told you this place was a zoo.
Come on, I'll take you home.
I can get a ride.
No lectures, I promise.
- He's still working with Matt?
- Not now.
What happened?
I'm okay. Some guy just
went off at the hospital.
- Jesus.
- Calm down.
- Gonna get Matt worked up.
- He can handle big feelings.
- You an expert on my son now?
- Yes, I am.
- Vic.
- Mommy?
Mommy had an accident. I'll be okay.
Cassidy, go get your homework out.
- I'll help you in a minute.
- I can handle things here.
Because you're an expert
on my whole family now.
No.
You should come down to the
Barn, look at the mug books.
Is that a good idea? I mean,
he knows where you work.
What's to stop him from
coming back and hurting you?
I'm what's stopping him.
She picks him out, I find him...
...make sure he knows going
back isn't an option.
It's not worth it. I mean,
just leave it alone.
You know I wouldn't ask you to do
this if I didn't think it was safe.
I'll call you. We'll figure it out.
Fine. You let me know.
- Sir, Aurora's on the phone.
- Tell her I'm in a meeting.
Are you? Because I don't
like lying to people.
I'm in a meeting.
Whatever you say.
We heard dudes fighting or something.
Yeah?
Saw the gate. Merril always locks it.
- You guys did good, calling us.
- Thanks.
Hey, hey, hey, wait here.
Wait here, all right?
- I'll go right.
- All right, I'll flank left.
No.
Danny!
There's a Merril Jindrich,
runs the community center...
...says the name of the victim
is Klee Jones. Local kid.
- Banger?
- Kid had no ink.
No gang tags anywhere.
He painted this.
He's got others around
the neighborhood.
It's beautiful stuff.
I always wondered who the artist was.
Maybe we could get the Strike
Team and the Decoy Squad...
...to help us run down leads.
We don't know if it's
gang- or drug-related.
And I wanna give Walon
some more cooling-off time.
Right now all we have is a homicide.
This boy wasn't just murdered.
He was lynched. You better
know there's a difference.
I know. You two can handle it.
- How's the stomach?
- Doc's got me on scrips.
Listen. I can understand you
not wanting to say anything...
...in front of the others.
But if you took our missing cash...
- Vic.
- For any reason...
...I promise we'll make it all right.
Look, I didn't take it.
Okay, I just had to ask.
Well, you know what, man?
Ask someone else.
Where's your mom and dad?
Dead.
Me and Klee pretty much
raised each other.
You know of anyone who would
wanna hurt your brother?
People barely notice him.
He's so quiet.
- Everybody loved his paintings.
- We saw.
They're amazing.
Ask Gitana.
I bet she's got something
to do with this.
Who's that?
This Mexicali girl
Klee hooked up with.
Her ex-boyfriend, all his friends,
they're straight up gangsters.
Los Profetas.
Klee was different.
I mean, not all about
getting at my ass and tits.
I mean, we'd talk about stuff.
Art, love, you know, life shit.
He made me realize, you know,
I could do better for myself.
Better than Neron?
We understand your ex-boyfriend
was a member of Los Profetas.
- Neron's a Cristo boy.
- Didn't work out?
He wanted me to go to church.
Meanwhile, he's on
the street thugging.
Klee's sister thinks that
your gang affiliations...
...might have something
to do with his death.
A lot of the gangs was pissed about
him painting over their tags.
Maybe Neron got jealous,
you dating a black guy.
I'm fine...
...but I'm not killing-fine.
I gotta ask you something...
I counted right the first time.
I counted right the last time
and I didn't take the money.
Lem said you asked.
You ask Shane yet?
Sir.
I have Aurora.
No, I have her here.
Any leads on the lynching?
Claudette and Dutch are on it.
Anyone in custody?
Just witnesses. Why?
People are terrified.
The black leadership's convening
a rally at the Hope Center.
- You need to go.
- It's a crime scene, not a photo op.
This isn't for the cameras.
You've to tell them that you
have everyone protected.
You make it sound
like I'm checked out.
The last thing we need is for a
dark-horse black candidate...
...to capitalize on this.
Run as an Independent.
Crazier things have
happened in this state.
Well, I'm not worried.
I've given you space to get
through whatever this is.
If you don't want to tell me what the
problem is, I'll find out another way.
Sir, you need to take this call.
We heard some of the
gangs were upset...
...because his murals
covered their tags.
He got some threats, talk mostly.
I think some of the gangs dug his
stuff. It just wasn't cool to say so.
Now what?
Do I really wanna know?
Father Zavala. Stabbed five times.
Must have come out from the sacristy.
Wounds are to the back and neck.
Any witnesses?
- Just the calling card.
- One-Niner payback for Klee Jones.
- Klee wasn't a banger.
- This is bigger than gang beefs.
He was a black boy
hanging from a tree.
The One-Niners think the Los
Profetas are responsible.
Zavala was their spiritual counsel.
Bring in the Strike Team.
Track down the Decoy
Squad and use them too.
Now that we know it's gang related?
- Vic, we got trouble.
- What's up?
It's the money-train fed.
He was asking me where
Aceveda and Dutch are.
- What's he want?
- Nothing we do.
Yeah, they told him to wait upstairs.
Detective, your team's
needed right away.
- Any inside info on Los Profetas?
- Killers with a conscience.
Got their piece of the street,
usually keep to themselves.
- It's biblical with these cats.
- Which means eye-for-an-eye time.
You cover the priest. Dutch and I'll
stay with the hanging.
Hey, look, in this hood, if
a black kid ends up dead...
...it's because a deal went
bad and someone's pissed off.
Guilty until proven white?
Yeah, maybe we should get
the ACLU to solve it.
We'll look under our rocks,
you look under yours.
These guys can't hear
anything right now.
Let's check out the Niners first.
You're getting some help. Well it's nothing.
Good decision. We definetely take care you guys.
What's up, Tob?
What's this, "Bring your
daddy to work" day?
Community outreach.
Neighborhood's in mourning.
I see that.
- Take the Shriners outside.
- All right, let's go, pops. Let's go.
Let's talk.
Give up the booth, Twizzy.
- Where's Kern at?
- I think he's in Prague, touring.
19 Playaz, huh?
- One-Niners funding that tour?
- We're creative partners.
Kern's put a lot of
faith in you guys.
Bet he's gonna be pretty disappointed
when he finds out you knifed the priest.
Oh, You're gonna be disappointed
when you find out we didn't.
No? Then who wrote
"One-nine" across his face?
He was tagged, dude.
What kind of crew you running here, Tob?
One hand don't know who the
other hand's stabbing?
Look, if one of mine
did it, I'll find out.
Make sure you give
him a medal for it.
Look, man. People loved that kid's murals,
all right. But I didn't order no hit on no priest.
But at least now the Prophets know
what it's like to lose a local hero.
You wanna tell me why you were
breaking bread with the thugs?
- Like he said, community outreach.
- You went to them for protection?
- Don't make me dig deeper.
- You see that billboard?
Can you read it? I can't.
Decade ago, this whole
block was black-owned.
Now me, Perry, all that's left.
Latin gangs hit my liquor store
19 times in the past year.
You think paying out to the
One-Niners isn't robbery?
Banger gets shot in a
drive-by, that's one thing.
You put on the colors, you
live and die the life.
But that boy, the painter,
he was just trying to do good.
You know, we got grandsons
coming up in this neighborhood.
One-Niners might be the only thing
keeping them from the noose.
You wanna feel safe, you come to me.
I heard that for the first time
40 years ago, after Watts.
Been hearing it ever since from
you boys, every few years.
Los Profetas didn't rope that guy.
Is that what the Niners think?
Is that why they
killed Father Zavala?
Your ex-girlfriend had
nothing to do with it?
Gitana?
Gitana was just a hit,
like nothing real.
You think going to confession once a week
exempts you from being a shitbag low life, Neron?
Klee Jones saw an ugly world, tried
to make it a little more beautiful.
He gave back. What'd you give?
What's everybody getting
so torn up about?
There's dudes getting dead out
there every day.
This dude...
...was lynched.
- I thought he was hung?
- Lynching is being hung.
- You ever read a history book?
- I tried not to.
Lynching's what they used
to terrorize the ex-slaves.
That's how the Klan
dealt with race-mixers.
If I'm gonna do somebody...
...I'm not gonna waste my time look for
no tree and a rope...
...when there's a million
guns lying around.
You tell Los Profetas,
if he starts retribution,
I will shut down all your street trade
and lock all of you up.
David.
You gonna shut down all their street trade and
lock them up? How you gonna follow up on that threat?
We got a rally in two hours,
and I don't want bloodshed.
Using that guy as your errand
boy is a short-term fix.
That's all we got time for.
Now get him out of here so
he can pass on the message.
Look what crawled out of the gutter.
Thought you guys were neck-deep in
that homeless-torching thing?
- Six days of undercover setup gone to shit.
- Why, what happened?
Claudette brought us
for this lynching.
Why?
It's pure gangland.
It's not a Decoy thing.
I'm sure she's got a plan.
Why the hell did you pull us off?
I want Trish and Annie
inside this the community rally.
You want my team pressing a crowd?
We had two homicides that created
enough racial tension...
Three homeless dead, and a fourth
one's gonna be toast...
- ... because you can't keep your finger off.
- Stop that right there.
Last week you tanked a major case, now
you want us into mall security?
- It's bullshit.
- I made a mistake.
I start digging in your
jacket, I won't find a few?
None that almost killed a cop.
If you can't find it within
yourself to work with me, fine.
You're docked.
Catch up on paperwork.
You signing off on this?
The job gets done when we trust
the decisions of our superiors.
- If he's out, we're all out.
- There's a chair.
There's six weeks of F.I.'s to file.
Mr. Rabinowitz?
I thought you were a doctor. I've
been waiting here 40 minutes.
- You were mugged?
- Corman Street.
This man, he jumps from
nowhere with a pipe...
- ...yells, "Give me your money."
- And you did?
Yes. And then he smashed my knee.
Took my streimel.
- He didn't have to hit you.
- What did I say?
When these things happen,
we must be strong.
- Can you give us a description?
- Asian, black hair.
Had a bandage on his arm.
Bandage?
Our arrest percentages are down
30 percent since we've been here.
We never had this kind interference
at Wilshire.
- Yeah, it's not right.
- We gotta get free again.
This team is the
assistant chief's baby.
Phillips will listen to me.
I just need a witness.
Look, I don't wanna be the one
responsible for letting you slip away.
It'll all be off the record.
Phillips just needs to know
that I'm not overreacting.
He does that sometimes.
- I can relate.
- You can count me in as a witness.
Hold on, hold on.
You really want out?
Okay.
I'll back you up. But you
gotta do the right thing.
I need Trish and Annie
to work the rally.
My guys are the wrong shade of black.
Hey, Vic, you got a sec?
They're all yours.
We just took a mugging call at Mission Cross,
sounds like seem the guy who attacked your wife.
- Any leads?
- I'm tracking the stolen credit cards.
- Let me know.
- Okay.
This guy hurt Corrine.
He can't come in
feeling good about that.
What's the favor?
He turns up...
...before you bring
him in, you call me.
Okay.
Ready?
You bet.
We appreciate your support
and your concern.
Our purpose for being here today...
...is not to just to talk about
this travesty that's happened...
...but um, to create a forum...
...for our awareness, answers.
Right now I'd like to turn over
the mike to Reverend Leeman.
Would you all be kind enough
to join hands, please?
Lord Jesus, we ask you to guide
our hearts and our minds.
Renew our faith, O Lord,
and open our eyes....
I hear you're responsible for having
Trish and Annie change their minds.
Walon was way out of line.
Thanks.
No problem.
Now, what do you guys got?
Not much conversation, but spotted
six sporting One-nine ink.
- Couple baby bangers.
- Four of them with unnatural bulges.
Okay, point them out to my guys.
They'll be the first ones
we jump if this goes ugly.
Okay.
It's all stirred up, isn't it?
- Yeah.
- Hey, Vic.
Sorry, boys, crusade's been canceled.
Ain't no holy war, homes.
- Just come to listen.
- You're too smart for this, Suvuto.
Come on, why don't you guys get in
your cars and bounce on out of here?
Ladies and gentlemen,
stay where you are.
Let the police officers do their job.
This Captain Aceveda is right...
Hey, ése, you got balls coming
here and break up our rally.
They're not looking for a fight,
neither are you.
No, we're just looking for
a priest-killer, homes.
- Anybody hurt?
- Everyone clear this area now.
...or you will be arrested,
clear the area now.
- You got a name for me?
- Yeah, I got a lot of names for you.
- Keep that sense of humor.
- Why are you locking me up, man?
We was there like anybody else, man.
No one else was jamming clips
into semi-nines, dude.
What you talking about man? Was the thorn heads
came up in there looking for blood and shit.
Why don't you talk through the fence,
maybe some racial harmony will break out.
- Man, you ain't nothing but a rat.
- What's up?
We found firecracker scraps.
That's what incited the shootings.
Pol Com and the archbishop
have riot fears.
They're pressuring us
to bring in the FBI.
- Put the National Guard on standby.
- That's a bad move.
- Sends a message we've lost control.
- So we haven't?
We'll solve these, calm the waters.
How much time before
the feds show up?
The chief wants me reporting
and from here the next 24 hours.
That buys us some time.
Let's see where we are by then.
I sense some disharmony
between you and Tobar.
- Kern keeps us civilized.
- Kern's in Europe.
- I should've come to you first.
- Come to me about what?
I gave Tobar the chance to give up
the Niner who offed the priest.
He blew it. I'm making
you the same offer.
Okay, where's my upside?
When you give up the
killer, with some proof...
...I'll get you your
boys out of lockup.
Let you do business rent-free.
Come on, Mackey. Everybody
knows you've been shut down.
You're not on the street
enough to landlord.
I'm getting the keys
to the city back.
Spoke to Lem and Ronnie.
When you gonna ask me about the cash?
Don't have to. None of us
took it, none of us spent it.
Trail won't lead back to us.
Yeah, I believe Lem and Ronnie too.
But that seven grand didn't
just spontaneously combust.
And now Aceveda's pulling his
marked-money list from the safe.
He's hooking the Treasury
guy up with Rodriguez.
Nothing's gonna lead back to us.
Okay. But if those flagged
bills have anything to do...
...with our missing cash...
...I'd sure like to know who
the hell's spending it.
Rodriguez, I thought you were pulling
those like-crime stats for me?
Sorry. Wagenbach's
working the hanging.
I got stuck working this
Armenian-mob thing.
I'll be in the car, we better hurry.
It's a long trip. Place closes at 4.
- Where you headed?
- Some bank in Indio.
- Where the hell's that?
- Palm Desert.
Sounds hot.
How did our cash end
up in the desert?
It's not from the 20
grand Diagur took.
Those marked bills were scooped up.
What gang's running meth through
that part of the state these days?
I don't know. Aceveda and the chief had us
out of the loop the last few months.
Street sweeps and dime-bag
bust quotas let us lay low.
Laying low's kept us in the dark.
We gotta get back to basics.
Plug back into the street intel.
Make ourselves indispensable
to the department again.
Best defense is a good offense.
How we gonna get Aceveda and
the chief to unleash us?
We won't have to. Walon's
gonna do it for us.
Meantime, as long as
there's no paper trail...
...leading from the marked bills
in Indio to us, we're golden.
Can you tell us how long
was Klee painting that mural?
About two weeks.
Did you ever see anyone harass
him, complain about it?
No.
- Did you ever talk to him at all?
- No.
He was right across the street for
two weeks. You never spoke to him?
He didn't come in, buy a soda?
Didn't pay the boy
that much attention.
Not an art lover, huh?
His painting's good and all that.
Just sends the wrong message.
What message is that, sir?
You know, in this neighborhood,
you gotta choose a side.
I'm black. That's my side.
Should've been his side too.
Hey, Vic.
We pulled a match from the books.
Tung Yung? I wish I
felt like laughing.
The other victim's in synagogue.
We're gonna need your wife
to make a positive ID.
Okay.
Circulate this. There's
a steak dinner in it...
...for the first one who gets me
a face-to-face with this prick.
My squad's being wasted here.
Aceveda twisted the chief's
arm to get you guys.
He's got us reporting to Wyms. Burying us
in extra layer commands. It's not working.
I got my problems with Wyms too.
Aceveda threw her in the deep end.
It's not her fault she's drowning.
You want me to unplug you...
...I'm gonna need a better
argument than a personality clash.
Providing for the homeless is
the mayor's pet project, right?
Yeah.
Might have a hard time explaining
to city hall...
...why your crack Decoy Squad was
pulled off the homeless-torching case...
...to file month-old robbery reports.
I'll need details.
That's my case.
We're admitted six days.
Perfect cover...
- What?
- I figured out...
...why Tobar was flaking
on giving up the knifer.
- Why is that?
- It was his boy, Link.
You'll find the blade and
bloody wear at his crib.
Good work.
Next thing, me and my team
are ear-deep in Barn shit.
Hey, we got a break.
Murder weapon. Blood-stained
Yankee jacket.
It's a slam-dunk.
- Great.
- This job's still only half done.
Where are we on the hanging?
All of the likely suspects
have come up clean.
He doesn't circulate
in the usual world.
We're hitting dead ends.
Decoy Squad hit a dead end too?
Father Zavala was killed
by gang violence.
- That's the Strike Team.
- I know what the Strike Team does.
You have the Decoy Squad
in your house also.
Why not put them on this?
Because they were docked
for insubordination.
- You docked them?
- I did.
We're keeping the lid on a
racial pressure-cooker.
- I know that.
- You put an entire special unit...
...on a dead Latino priest and docked the team
that could be solving the lynching of a black man?
- That's not the truth.
- The truth is whatever it looks like.
And this looks like racial
prioritizing, councilman.
- Come on.
- Yeah. yeah.
- About time you let us out of here.
- It's just long enough to do this.
Elias Linkletter, you're under arrest
for the murder of Father Oleos Zavala.
- This is shit.
- No. This is proof.
Tob, man, I didn't kill him.
I ain't killed no priest, Tob.
You can let this half go.
Except for that one.
Aiding and abetting.
Hey, man, you hurt us, you hurt Kern.
Kern's licking caviar off
a Czech girl.
He won't be too hurt.
- I want you to tell me what's wrong.
- Aurora...
I went to Rigoberto.
Spoke to him.
Whatever your secret is,
he's keeping it.
There's no secret.
You tell your cousin
but not your wife?
A less secure woman might
think there's someone else.
- Babe, I'm not screwing around.
- You're hiding something.
- Please let this go.
- What is it?
- Act like a husband.
- Please.
Just trust me.
- Trust me.
- Aurora.
I'm very scared, David.
Those guys I fought...
...one of them assaulted me.
But you're okay now.
They tied my hands.
And they made me get on my knees.
They made you...
...suck?
- Both of them?
- Just one of them.
You didn't.
Wait, you're a cop.
You're trained in...
I was alone. I was in... I was...
No, David.
How could you let that happen?
Because I wanted to live...
... for you.
I wanted to live for you and Sophia.
I can't talk about this here.
I never saw that knife...
...and I'd never be
wearing no Yankee rag.
I was born in Boston. Man, I'd
rather take a knife than wear N.Y.
I'm not sure if I'd use the Red
Sox defense in a Dodger town.
That was a horrible thing
they did to Klee Jones.
Lynching a brother's some wrong shit.
Maybe you wanted to
send him a message.
Make sure it didn't
ever happen again.
You got the right message,
but the wrong messenger.
No, we don't.
You stabbed Father Zavala
five times this morning.
No.
This morning?
- I was in my group.
- Group?
Anger therapy?
Kern's shrink?
Been learning to keep
my emotions in check.
He's probably lying about the therapy
sessions, at least when he got there.
The parish raised bail
for the Prophets.
One murder still unsolved and now
all the players are back in action.
Put Walon's team in the mix. Let them spend
the night on the street and see what they hear.
- You said you'd back me on that decision.
- Just do it, already.
Hey. Whatever's been eating at you
lately, don't take it out on her.
She's the main thing keeping this
place glued together.
- That's enough, Dutch.
- No.
You got her juggling a full detective
load plus this supervisory post.
Then hang her out to dry?
That's not leadership.
How's your detective load, Wagenbach?
Anything new on the sick
bastard raping grandmothers?
No.
Hey, Cobalt, how's business?
We're looking for a friend of yours.
An Asian guy trying to score painkillers.
- Aren't we all?
- Mind if we take a look inside?
Mind letting me see a warrant?
That's okay. We'll just
wait for him here.
Greet your customers.
Who you looking for?
He was around.
Tried to give me a ton of
Sudafed for a few Percocet.
- This is a cash-only slot.
- Where'd you send him?
A Thai cat sells scrips out of a
clinic on Hanover and Carmen.
Should be there in the morning.
Thanks.
His anger-management
alibi checks out.
He's got a shrink and eight fellow
hotheads who can account for his time.
How did the knife and bloody
sweatshirt get in his place?
I'll follow up on that.
I need a minute.
- What is it?
- I bet on the wrong scumbag.
How'd you do that?
You and Wyms have had me buried
over the last couple of months.
- I'm out of touch.
- Oh, so it's my fault?
- I'll bring in the right guy.
- Good.
But I'll never let this happen again.
I'm no good half in, half out.
Now, you gotta make a choice.
You either let me do what I do or I'll
pull the plug on the Strike Team.
Take my boys to another part of town.
- Lose the hardware! Lose it!
- Get on the table. On the table.
Drop it.
- What the hell's going on, Mackey?
- It's closing time.
My first task as the new landlord,
get rid of the old tenants.
This was not a part
of our transaction.
That deal went south the second you
screwed everyone in this room.
Screwed who?
Shit.
Seems you fingered a man
with an airtight alibi.
Pigs turning us against each other...
Shut up, bastard.
I can see I'm in the way.
What you talking about? You can't leave
me here with them, man.
I can't take you with me.
You're an innocent man.
Unless you got something
to confess, Twizzy.
I didn't do nothing.
Okay. Take care.
Vic, where you...?
All right. All right, Vic. All right.
How'd the knife and the Yankee
rag end up under Link's bed?
Not so sure if I remember
all the details now.
Let me refresh you on the math.
You framed number two, which
implicated number one...
...which bounced you from number
three to the new number one.
And that gets you zero.
All right, bastard. Let's let Tobar
and Link finish the interrogation.
Let's go clubbing.
Hey, man, look what we
found at Twizzy's place.
It's the same rope
Klee was hanging from.
Shit.
No one's gonna save your ass, Twizzy.
That camera hasn't worked in months.
Now you talk to us or you can talk
to your boys between beatings.
I strung him. You damn right I did.
Someone's got to be the martyr here.
It might as well be me.
Why?
That Rainbow Coalition
shit was crushing us.
Kern and Tobar caved on me.
They punked out.
Wanna strike deals with the Lats.
So you decided to set
off the racial bomb.
The priest?
I wanted to see the Prophets cry.
Fuel the war.
Get the Black back.
Farmtown...
...Jack Uzis...
...the local businessmen...
...I got them all sitting down.
Talking about working together.
I did.
Black-on-black lynching.
Is that better or worse?
Worse.
Hi.
- What's that?
- Open it.
- It's locked.
- It's funny, you know.
I never really lock my lockbox.
Okay.
The reason I never lock it...
...is because I can never remember
where I put the key.
But somebody locked it.
I was looking for some
old photos, some stuff.
I don't know anything about
your family or...
You know, I really know a
lot about your family.
I called your mom in Indio.
She told me about the $7000
care package that you sent.
You'd disappear at night.
I saw you take the
key a couple times.
So you decided that you
would steal from me?
I found a receipt for
a storage facility...
...with your handwriting
and a fake name.
You'd been lying to me. What
did you expect me to do?
Jesus Christ. You have no idea
what kind of trouble this is.
You know what trouble
I've been going through?
- Why are you hiding money from me?
- You stole from me!
You stole from me!
That trunk was filled with cash.
I just took what I needed.
For us. Us.
What happened to us?
- You gonna lie to your child too?
- Hey, don't you go turn this around.
My mother's a goddamn cancer.
She was being evicted.
She would've showed
up on our doorstep.
I didn't want her to ruin this.
You shouldn't have looked
into those trunks.
Is there money in all those trunks?
- Is it drug money?
- You don't get to ask that question.
- But it's from your job, right?
- Just stop asking.
Should I ask Vic instead?
Is it Vic's money?
- Did you steal it from him?
- No.
- Then where did it come from?
- Just forget that you saw it.
- How am I supposed to do that?
- Look, l...
You just do it.
Hey.
Look, you don't take any more cash.
Don't breathe a word
about this to anybody.
Now we gotta figure out what to have your mother
say in case people start asking questions.
- Who's gonna ask her questions?
- The money wasn't supposed to be spent.
When it comes to money,
we can't trust her.
Then we're gonna have to
find a way to control her.
Because if this money
gets traced back to me...
...this is life-and-death shit...
...for all of us.
Is this the man who attacked you?
- Yeah. That's him.
- Great.
The old Jew he mugged has
been in temple lockdown.
Now we can finally arrest this prick.
Did I say something wrong?
- I'm sorry, are you Jewish?
- Someone keyed Owen's car.
Scratched "Stay away"
across the trunk.
You think I did it?
It had to have been done
last night before I left.
If I wanted you to stay away, I
wouldn't scratch it in your Volvo.
- You'd scratch it across my face?
- Owen.
- What are you telling this guy?
- Nothing I can't see for myself.
You keep your mouth shut
in front of my kids.
- Don't yell at him.
- Stop it.
I wrote it.
- Cassidy.
- No, I'll do it.
I don't want him here.
Owen makes your mommy happy, honey.
Why can't you make Mommy happy?
I'd be hurt if I were you too.
I will always be your dad.
And your mommy will
always be your mommy.
That's never gonna change.
Everything is changing.
Yes?
The Decoy Squad's being
transferred to South Central.
- When?
- Tomorrow.
- Who?
- It's the assistant chief's call.
I didn't fight it. It
wasn't gonna work.
We can still get done what we
need to with the Strike Team.
Vic and his guys are going back to
full-time anti-gang and vice status.
You're putting them
back on the street?
I'm no longer running the team.
I had no time to consult with you.
It all went down pretty quickly.
You, uh...
You'll resume your regular
detective rotation.
So strike one and I'm out?
It was my fault. I had
you half in, half out.
- And I should've just let...
- You're the boss.
You don't have to
explain your decision.
Charges against your
boys have been dropped.
I heard.
You also hear that
we know who did it?
Tell Los Profetas no
more retribution.
That's God's decision.
God's decided to put
me back in business.
My streets, my rules.
- Niners ain't playing by the rules.
- Twizzy was a rogue.
Kern, Tobar never would
have let that happen.
We still got pain.
Twizzy will be in county
until his hearing.
That'll give you a few weeks
to get someone inside.
Stop the pain.
Anything after that,
commit any sins...
...I'll be nailing you to a cross.
Thank God you caught the guy.
Yeah, people are relieved.
The election should
be smooth sailing.
Good.
I just came home to change.
Okay.
He's early.
Tung Yung?
Stay down.
What's the target?
Blue house.
Russians. Fresh from the Kremlin.
Moving in, moving weight.
China white.
I got some bad news, Boris.
Air just tastes better
today, doesn't it?
Yeah.
Vic, l....
What?
It's good to be back.
Thank you so much.
- Where do you want him?
- Put him in 2.
Knock, knock.
- Put your hands up! Turn in up!
- Right there! On the ground!
On the ground!
Right there!
Down, down.
Welcome to the neighbourhood.