Previously on "The Shield".
They killed these Armenians
looking for our money-train cash.
There's four people
who know we took that money.
They're all sitting right here.
My office instituted a sting operation.
What kind of sting operation?
In San Jose, the Armenians were extorting
a local businessman.
He allowed us to insert $50,000
of marked, traceable bills
into his payment to the Armenians so,
any of these marked bills show up,
they might lead you to your killers.
Hey. I'm getting the feeling you're not
appreciating the promotion I gave you.
It doesn't matter to what I agree.
Garza calls the shots.
I just need proof
he ordered the hit on this Calva guy
and the throne
and the crown are all yours.
Put this with the rest
of the Money Train stash.
It's 20 grand light.
Byz Lats' overhead, I guess.
- Better than losing the whole hundred.
- The way I figure it.
Victim's name is lsabel Nelson,
raped by a lone male.
Guy was waiting in the house naked
when she came home.
Isabel's 73.
I need you to work it out with Shane.
- Tell him.
- I'm gonna talk to him too.
But I'm asking you,
take one for the team here.
He's been my best friend for seven years.
You really think he's gonna push me aside
for some darkie?
Get off!
Here she is.
What's going on?
Jesus, no one's telling us anything.
I talked to Dr. Thiel
and Tavon's condition is grave...
traumatic brain damage.
He's got a tough road.
Can we see him?
He's in ICU. It's family only.
He's on my team.
If he takes a turn either way,
I'll let you know.
- Yeah.
- Did you get my messages?
No. What's going on?
Tavon got into an accident, man.
Hit a parked car full speed.
He might not make it.
Man.
Listen, we're at Mission Cross.
You gotta get down here.
Yeah. I...
I kind of had a rough night myself.
I mixed it up with this guy
at the Three of Clubs.
I gotta take this other call.
- lf you can make it, you should come.
- Okay.
We gotta clean this up.
- Hello?
- I called you.
What's the problem, ma'am?
I think my ex-boyfriend's in the house.
Lyle Dockman. He's been harassing me.
My bedroom light was off
when I went to work.
Did you get a restraining order
out on him?
Yes. It just made him madder.
All right, we'll check it out.
Police.
Anyone in the house?
I'll check the upstairs.
Ma'am, stay back, please.
Bedroom's clear.
My God.
Danielle!
Halt! Police!
Halt!
You okay?
Yeah.
Is he gone?
I'm here. What?
Sorry about Tavon.
What do you want?
I need you to sweep the Alvarado Corridor.
- Looking for?
- Cruisers, loiterers.
There have been complaints
from business owners and citizens.
You want me for something real,
I'll be at the hospital.
The doctors said they won't know anything
for a couple of days.
I'm sorry it happened
but there's still work to do.
I'm a detective not a janitor.
- Get your units to do your sweeping.
- I'm giving you the broom.
Strike Team is a special unit.
All you've done since your promotion
is jam us up with bullshit gigs.
Maybe with Gilroy
you could pick your special cases,
but now it goes:
Chief Bankston to Aceveda to me to you.
You don't like that pecking order,
take it up the ladder.
See who is out of a job.
Alvarado Corridor?
Till I tell you otherwise.
You all right?
Bulb blew out.
THE SHIELD
- Shane!
- I got it.
Hang on.
Coming.
- Sorry, I was on my way...
- Forget it.
Wyms has us on a shit sweep.
Alvarado.
Jesus. Someone clocked you.
- Dude, who kicked your ass?
- It was this guy...
This drunk asshole
was pawing me in the bar and,
Shane told him to get lost
and him and his friends
jumped him in the bathroom.
There was more than one guy?
No, it was mainly one guy.
I mean, the other guys
just stood there and watched.
How is Tavon doing?
Did he come by here tonight?
Tavon? No, why would he?
He said he was gonna mend fences.
It's just us.
Laundry night.
Everything else all right?
Yeah. I'm good.
I'm taking care of him.
Stay home.
I don't want you showing up at work
looking like you got bitchslapped.
Fiesta siesta.
Anybody still here in a minute
gets run in.
You heard the man. Let's pack it up
- party people!
- Come on.
Thought this was a free country.
Got a curfew in this part of town, homes.
Not for me. I'm over 21.
What do you think?
About 14 coats of high-end enamel?
Let's see.
Yo, man. I'm gone, man.
- Where were you tonight around 10:00?
- Jogging.
I do three miles every night after work.
You weren't doing a 100-yard dash
through your ex-girlfriend's backyard?
Elena? I can't go within 1000 feet of her.
Or call her, but you've been
leaving messages on her machine.
Before the restraining order.
It's a crime to want another chance?
- She's not giving you another chance.
- Not yet.
- Not ever.
- Someone was in her house tonight.
- Is she okay?
- She's fine.
Can anyone verify
you were jogging tonight?
You'd have to ask around.
Okay, well, we're watching over Elena.
And now we're watching you.
Problema, amigo?
This is your 10th citation
for cruising in the last four months.
I juice up cars.
Humming out here with my baby's
the only advertisement I got.
Try the Yellow Pages,
because we're bringing the car in.
- When do I get it back?
- About a month or two.
- After you see a judge, pay a fine.
- Well, take care of her till then.
Every cent I made the last five years
I got wrapped up on her.
Really? I would have pegged you
as more of a mutual-fund guy.
What do I gotta do to keep my wheels?
Flip me someone juicier than you.
Here's her ride.
Wait. This vato, Aramis.
I call her twice a month.
I remember her birthday.
- Her only son.
- So you're taking her?
Seen Claudette?
She and Dutch just caught one.
Another possible elderly rape victim.
What do you need?
She's got me working
the Alvarado Corridor next few days.
Right. Sweeping duty.
Last night, I'm tagging this guy.
We're about to tow away his Hot Wheels,
he spills about a guy sneaking contraband
into Chino Prison for his gang buddies.
What kind of contraband?
Drugs, cigs, xxxx rings,
weapons of mass destruction, who knows?
You checking into it?
I was looking for Claudette to see
if I should stick with cruiser duty.
Follow up on this for the time being.
Wherever you want me.
- Gentlemen, what do we got?
- B&E, robbery.
Fits your rapist profile, though.
Elderly woman, living alone.
- You read my memos?
- Watch C.O. makes us.
- Did the victim call it in?
- No, I didn't.
I did.
Detective Wyms and Wagenbach.
Patty Klopp. My mother, Luann.
They broke in last night.
I stopped by this morning
and noticed some Hummels were gone.
Couple of tchotchkes. So what?
Someone broke into your home, Ma.
- You have to report that.
- And now you have.
She's supposed to be watching
her sugar levels.
Anything taken from the bedroom?
Not that I know of.
When did the robbery occur?
Last night.
Came home around...
9:00 from the movies.
You see anybody?
Just saw my things missing.
You weren't afraid?
I've lived in this neighborhood
for 40 years.
Your daughter says she's trying
to get you to Encino.
You'll have to kill me
before I retire to the valley.
You got something special in mind
for the ride back?
Funny.
The compulsive eating, the odd,
distracted behavior.
I think Luann was raped.
Well, yeah, she's a tough, old broad,
but I saw it too.
You are agreeing with me?
I'm agreeing that she loses her dignity
if she admits she was attacked.
Her dignity and her independence.
Speaking of losing your dignity...
The bed was stripped.
There was nothing in the clothes hamper.
Whatever you find in there
is gonna be too contaminated to test.
It's too bad.
Why do you throw out
a perfectly good set of sheets?
To bury the truth.
Wonder how many other buried sheets there
are out there.
Here's Aramis.
Byz Lats are showing initiative.
Diagur's running them better
than I thought.
Yo, Ronnie, you see him?
Guy with the cigarettes? Yeah, I got him.
That's good.
Either this guy
is sneaking shit into Chino
or he needs the world's largest patch.
Let's see where he takes us.
We can't provide 24-hour protection
to every woman with an ex with a temper.
Sir, I did some checking up
on this bastard.
The last ex who got
a restraining order on him,
left a good job in Cleveland
to move to New Hampshire
just to disappear from this guy.
She was sure that he would kill her.
This one feels real to me, sir.
Look, Danny's right.
This one feels real.
Okay, we can escort her to and from work.
Extra patrols.
You got one week for the guy to violate
the order before I pull the plug.
- All right. Thank you, sir.
- Don't thank me.
She should be thanking you.
I got 29 B & E's of elderly women.
Eleven in the last six months.
Called the hospitals, they'll give us
a heads up if anyone fits that profile.
What about your new promotion?
You sure you got time
to help me on this one?
For this? Yeah, I'm all yours.
Yeah? Ever hear of this guy?
This "Mueller's Geographical Profiles"?
That's the criminologist from Duke?
Doctor of Criminal Logistics.
Takes data on serial violent crimes,
victims, nature of the assault...
Generates the most likely location
of where the perpetrator lives or works.
Needs three confirmed cases
to work up a preliminary profile.
- We've only got one victim confirmed.
- Two if Luann comes clean.
You think Aceveda will spring for it?
It's expensive.
No. Let's find numbers two and three.
Then we'll stick him with the bill.
You already made arrests?
Caught them exchanging packages
of smokes and drugs,
along with 7,500 in cash.
Guess that's the smuggling rate
these days.
- Good work.
- Banger puts together care packages.
The white guy
is a frozen-food delivery man
who drops off at Chino twice a week.
What are you working on exactly?
I got a tip from a cruiser last night
about a guy sneaking swag
into the state pen.
Shouldn't be hard to get Joe Trucker
to roll on cholo and vice versa.
- You moved off the Alvarado Corridor?
- Yeah.
Couldn't find you,
so I moved up the ladder.
So I had some cigarettes.
We're not talking about
a couple cartons of Marlboros.
We nabbed you handing off
20 thumbs of heroin too.
Must be the old man's.
I learned in school to just say no.
You take the orders, gather the shit,
hand them off to Fred
who sneaks it in with the frozen peas.
Am I right?
- We got you dead on rights, man.
- On all your wrongs.
Look.
I spoke to the DA.
If you cooperate, I can make sure
that you do your time at Chino again
- with all your fellow banditos.
- Else, who knows,
maybe you end up
someplace chilly like Shasta.
Can I go home now?
Sorry. It's gonna be a little while.
What's the problem?
We just talked to Aramis.
He told us the whole thing.
The twice a week drop-offs you make
at Chino State Correctional Facility.
I'm a delivery man. That's my job.
There was heroin
in this week's care package.
I don't look at what's in the packages.
But you knew it was wrong.
I should go home now.
- My wife is making dinner.
- Easy. It's all right.
Fred.
You're under arrest. You understand that?
No. That's not right.
If you can confirm
who receives this stuff on the inside
maybe we can make things
a little easier on you.
No. This is a mistake.
This can't happen.
I'm not a criminal.
The Strike Team just made a bust
that included $7,500 in cash.
I need you to run the serial numbers
of the bills against these numbers.
Again with this?
Let me know if you get any matches
and then return that list straight to me.
Why do you have me doing
such menial things for you?
- Because you're my assistant.
- I could be so much more to you.
With the election and everything.
I have a campaign staff for that.
They don't know what they are doing.
You've no idea the mistakes I fix
before they land on your desk.
And I appreciate it, but for now, please.
Just check the numbers on that list
against the money in evidence.
- You okay?
- It's Layla.
She reported a robbery five months ago
and after a lot of handholding,
just admitted she was raped.
- Jesus. This guy...
- She tell you anything that will help?
No condoms, no climax.
- A lot of cuddling.
- That makes two confirmed.
I struck out on my end.
We need one more.
I don't remember anybody snooping around.
Delivery guy?
Anybody that seemed suspicious?
In this neighborhood?
Try to find someone
who doesn't look suspicious.
The reason we ask, Luann,
is because there is a man
who is breaking into homes
and sexually assaulting women.
- Sexually?
- I'm flattered, detective.
He's targeting women your age.
- What are you talking about?
- Did someone hurt you?
Of course not.
Thank God.
- I pulled Tavon's accident report.
- Thanks for doing that.
You know, witnesses saw
the car swerving a couple blocks
before he hit that parked car.
- Before?
- Yeah.
- Is Tavon a drinker?
- I don't think so.
Which direction was the car going in?
North on Perry.
North?
Thanks.
Hey.
I thought you don't want me coming in.
I thought you were gonna come alone.
She wasn't sure I was good to drive.
- Thoughtful.
- Yeah.
What's up?
Tavon was headed away from your place.
Witnesses saw his car swerving all
over the road, before he hit the car.
Toxi report shows no drugs or alcohol.
That's weird.
What do you think happened?
Don't know yet.
Don't have all the facts.
There's something missing.
Like a coffee table or a painting.
Look, he came over.
Gave me this backhanded apology.
We had some words.
He jumped me.
And I tagged him back
with a pretty good shot.
How good and where?
- To the back of the head.
- The back of the...
He has brain trauma.
It was from an accident
that happened miles away from my place.
He was swerving all over the road
before the crash.
Your blow probably caused it.
You could face charges.
- What did you hit him with?
- A paperweight or something.
Look, he was all over me.
Where were you during all this?
I was doing laundry in the basement.
- Really? Whites or colors?
- She wasn't there.
All right?
This thing was all me.
- Hold on.
- Here's your list back.
- Thank you.
- Got two matches.
- What?
- Two of the bills.
Their serial numbers were on the list.
I wrote which ones down for you.
Where are you taking him?
Interrogation.
- I'll meet you upstairs.
- Sure thing.
We miss a piece of the puzzle
putting together Aramis?
No. We just need to talk to him
on an unrelated matter.
I'll let you guys get back
to the Alvarado Corridor.
Thanks.
Who is the suit?
His lD said Treasury.
That's the second T-fed in our house
in two weeks.
What's Treasury want from our collar?
Aramis is one of Diagur's tenientes.
You think that Aceveda knows about
the corners we cut with Diagur
to get those guns back?
One way to find out.
Care about that.
Just tell us where you got the 7,500
in cash you gave to the delivery guy.
I already made a deal with the other cop.
Ain't gotta rat on my boys.
Your crime is now
under federal investigation.
That's why Agent Nell is here.
Which means any previous deal,
got null and void.
Bullshit. My ticket's punched to Chino.
It's punched wherever we say it is.
Captain Aceveda has been checking money
confiscated in arrests.
So?
Two of the bills you had
in your possession were marked.
They were stolen from
an Armenian money-laundering ring.
Holy shit.
We've been waiting for it to show up.
Guess what? It showed up in your hands.
- Our money is marked?
- No way.
- I don't know anything about...
- Aramis said he got it from Diagur.
We got our bag back from Diagur
20 grand light.
We are starting at square one Aramis.
Who did you get the money from?
- I don't know where I got it from.
- Not good enough.
Whoever stole that money
killed two Armenians to get it.
We're gonna tie someone to these murders.
You want it to be you...
or someone else?
I really don't think
you want the death penalty
for something you didn't do.
Go!
I got a sick feeling, man.
It's all crashing.
Not if we steer it in the right direction.
Our money is marked?
Some of it? All of it?
- We don't know, man.
- Where are we going?
Silence the smoking gun.
We're looking for Diagur.
- Who are you faggots?
- Watch your mouth.
We're the guys busting you
for possession of an illegal substance.
- Where's Diagur?
- Who?
Today's not the day.
I just need to talk to him.
Where is he?
Yeah. You give me a message,
I'll pass it on to him.
How long you been out of Terminal lsland?
Not long enough.
You don't tell me where your boss is at,
you gonna be jumping back.
Home is where the heart is.
Huff the pipe, asshole. Just take a hit.
Take a hit.
Take it.
Take it! Goddamn it!
- Join the party, sweetheart. Come on.
- He's at Yolanda's.
One street over.
Brown house with the Madonna.
- Diagur?
- Si.
- Donde?
- En el cuarto.
- Jesus Christ.
- Get out!
It's okay. Okay, I know him.
- How old are you?
- Old enough.
Glad Mom has such a firm grasp on things.
Wait outside.
- Let's go.
- I need my clothes.
What you doing breaking my freak, yo?
You got a Byz Lats lawyer
on your speed dial?
- One of my boys has an uncle.
- Call him.
Get him down
to the Farmington station house now.
- What's there?
- Your prison delivery boy, Aramis.
If he's doing things,
it's without me knowing.
I'm all over your Chino game.
Unless you want my boss all over you,
you get your lawyer down there
and make sure he zips it.
Now.
Someone left a rose
in Elena's mailbox this afternoon.
Don't you have
more important things to do?
Actually, unlawful use of a mailbox
is a federal offense.
We got done talking to your boss.
Technically, you were on the clock.
Supposed to be making business calls.
You got proof it was me?
For future proof, your boss
has agreed to monitor all your calls
and your online activity here at work.
- You can't do that.
- No. But she can.
You can either spend your 9 to 5 stalking
or you can spend it working.
You can't do both.
Listen, lady.
This is my job.
Not for long
if you don't leave Elena alone.
Have a nice day.
I'll talk to you later.
- Lawyer is on his way.
- Good.
You know, you said before,
you didn't have my back.
Why you helping me now?
Feds are buzzing around the money
you gave to Aramis.
It's tied to a robbery.
Somebody ripped off the Armenian mob.
Well, man, I ain't suicidal.
The Armenians find out
that you guys are suspects
the Byz Lats will be in up to their necks
and severed feet.
I'm just trying to prevent a war.
Where did you get the cash?
Who knows? It comes in a dozen ways.
Anybody asks, that's your best answer.
You give Aramis anything
besides the 7,500?
Yeah.
- Fifteen grand.
- You handed it to him personally?
- Think I trust some flunky with it?
- Your fingerprints could be on it.
- Any idea where he stashed it?
- Yeah. In his freezer.
- My idea.
- Original.
Get somebody down to his place
to pick it up.
You disappear for a couple of weeks.
Shit.
- He's back in the cage.
- He talked.
He goddamn talked.
Sarge.
Cold hard cash.
I'll run the serial numbers
against the master list.
I get this to the lab before 5:00
I can get fingerprint results by morning.
You coming?
He gave us permission to search his place.
I'm curious what else we might find here.
I'll call some units for a ride.
Diana Peabo.
She came into the ER last month.
Injuries sustained during a home robbery.
Her kids just brought her in again.
Allergic reaction.
Mixed up two of her meds.
They said that she's been
kind of out of it since the attack.
One of the nurses saw your bulletin.
Thank her for us.
It's a him, actually.
They're in Consultation.
How is Tavon?
He's the same.
Excuse me. Could I talk with you a moment?
Detective Wyms. Detective Wagenbach.
How's your mother?
She'll be just fine.
- What's this all about?
- We wondered if we could talk to her
about that robbery last month.
Why now?
We think your mother might be able
to help us find the person who did it.
It's not here.
Police! Don't move.
Keep your hands in the open.
Hey! Don't move! Don't make me do it, man.
Stop right there.
Put your hands in the air.
Don't make it worse for yourself.
Turn around.
On your knees, man.
Hey!
Hey, man.
Hey, don't make this mistake.
I'm a police officer.
So you a cop?
That mean you can do
whatever the hell you want?
Hey.
You can still get out of this.
Now you telling me what to do.
Hey, man,
you need to calm your friend down.
Tie him up. Tie him up with something.
Put out your hands.
Hurry up.
Don't throw your life away.
I ain't afraid of prison.
But you should be.
You ever...
suck a xxxx like a cell bitch, cop man?
Don't do this.
It's your turn to gag on something.
No.
Open up, sweetheart.
You wanna die instead?
No.
Captain.
That's great.
Probably had a limo come pick him up.
Can I get confirmation
on that pickup address?
There's no one here
at our current location.
Negative, 1-Tango-16. Unable to confirm.
Let's head out.
They're gone.
Let's see that mouth.
- El Presidente around?
- Captain Aceveda? No.
Where is he?
Conducting a search at a suspect's house.
Could you raise him on the horn for me?
I got an important question for him.
I'll try, but I've left two messages
for him in the last 10 minutes.
His cell-phone coverage is bad sometimes.
No.
Thanks.
Get your phone, man.
- What?
- Your phone.
I wanna get a Kodak of this.
Okay.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
I got it.
You don't remember anything else?
There's nothing about his face?
His height?
I'm gonna tell you something you're not
gonna like hearing very much Vince.
I know, as a son,
it's the last thing I'd wanna hear.
What's going on?
We think your mother wasn't just
knocked down by that guy last month.
We believe he may have
sexually assaulted her.
Sexually.
It would account for why
she's so distracted lately.
- That's a lot of pain to push down.
- We hope we're wrong.
Why don't you start by telling us
what happened that day?
I found her lying on the kitchen floor.
She couldn't stop crying.
- What else?
- Back window was broken.
She said a guy came in, knocked her down,
grabbed a few things, then ran.
She would've told me if...
Maybe she needed more time.
Yo, man, if he tells his boys, we're done.
You gonna say anything?
- No.
- Hey, you can't believe that shit.
What? You wanna kill him?
You do it.
You want it done...
you do it.
Hey, man.
I have a little girl.
I have a wife.
Mother.
Yo, man, you gotta do it.
- I'll watch.
- You've been wanting the juice, man.
Do it.
If your mother were here...
what would she tell you to do?
Not this kind of juice, bro.
Not this kind of juice.
It's the other cop. Let's go.
I'm in here.
Bust the door.
- It's locked. Try it again.
- I got it.
- He's here!
- Sweep it.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
- Clear.
- They got my gun.
- They?
Yeah.
- The two of them.
- Are you hurt?
No.
I was able to fight them off.
Mom.
I need you to tell me
what happened during the robbery.
- I told you everything I remember.
- Have you?
What else did he do to you?
Where are those police people?
He hurt you?
Stop it, Vincent.
Raped you?
Don't you say that.
Mom, did he?
Yes, he did.
Why didn't you tell me?
Mama, why?
Hold it.
- You see something?
- Maybe.
- Let's go.
- Yep.
- You can't keep me here.
- That's true.
You'll probably make bail
sometime tomorrow.
Trial won't be for another six months.
But in between,
every time you roll a stop sign,
I'm gonna hand you a ticket.
Every lunch break you take,
I'm gonna be sitting at the next table.
- Yeah, that's harassment.
- No, Lyle. That's stalking.
Hey, you okay?
Yeah, I had a little run-in.
No harm done.
Let's not waste any time on it.
Hey, what happened?
He fended off a couple of bad guys.
Miracle he hasn't called
a press conference yet.
She's in there alone
with her husband's service weapon.
My key wasn't working in the new lock.
- She shot at me when I opened the door.
- You okay?
Come on, I told you to stay in the car.
Luann.
Luann?
- Can you drop the gun?
- Put the gun down, Luann.
It's okay, sweetheart.
I know what happened to you.
That's our wedding.
You were very beautiful.
I was a size 4.
Can you tell me what happened to you?
He robbed me.
I didn't want to get robbed again.
Hey, Cassy.
Hi, Mr. Mackey.
- Cassidy, Owen said hello to you.
- Hey.
Sorry. She's struggling
with this whole thing.
It's okay.
Hey, little man.
I'm drawing a zoo.
- Hey, that's great, Matty.
- Corrine's in with Megan.
Hey.
- How did she do with Dr. Franks?
- You know shrinks.
You ask them one question,
they give you five back.
She's being quiet and a little stubborn.
He wants you and l to do sessions too.
One on one.
I want her to get all the help she needs
but me laying down on a couch?
- It's not gonna happen.
- Stubborn and incommunicative.
Wonder where she gets that from?
- How is Tavon doing?
- The last surgery gave him some hope.
The brain-tissue bruising
isn't bad as they thought.
- That's good.
- The next 48 hours should tell.
Good.
If he recovers, would he be able
to remember anything that happened?
I got him working on this
undercover assignment.
Well, he could remember every detail.
Or he could wake up and barely
recognize his own reflection.
If Tavon lives, he could remember
everything that happened.
If he dies, an autopsy could reveal
the blow to the head before the crash.
We'll figure it out, baby.
Chew on this, baby.
We just found out the feds
marked some of our money train cash.
- What?
- Part of a sting they're doing
on the Armenians.
- Shit.
- Deep.
And if that's not enough,
this accident leads back to you without us
getting self-defense on the books...
I.A.D. could be all over you
right at the time
we're gonna cash in on the money train.
So, what do we do?
Now it's "we."
Tell me the truth.
I did.
You had a fight.
- One of you hit him.
- It was self-defense.
If you both tell your story right now,
this could all go away.
Look, we gotta make a decision.
Right now.
Which road are we going down?
Look, everybody knew
Tavon and I had bad blood.
No, we gotta make this disappear.
We think this cuddler rapist
has been around for a while.
We've looked at like-crimes.
We've interviewed dozens of women.
We've confirmed three victims,
which is required for his analysis.
Mueller's results have been proven
accurate down to the square block.
We match this with known offenders,
we narrow our search dramatically.
Well, if this Mueller can help,
then let him.
Mueller isn't free.
- His fee is $5000.
- Right.
It can't happen.
We're really at a standstill on this.
Stranger perpetrator.
The victims could pile up
until he makes a mistake.
And so far, he hasn't made one.
Captain?
No. I said, no.
We don't have the money.
All right, roll up that rug.
Hit some yard sales,
pick up a new rug and a table.
Picture too.
Use cash.
I'll drop by this weekend
and help you patch that wall.
What did you hit him with?
Nice paperweight.
Put that in the truck with the rug.
It's a brand-new iron.
I washed it. It's clean.
We'll get a new one.
Put the broken table on my truck.
I'll dump that too.
This is dangerous,
you know that, don't you?
It's not my fault that he crashed.
You mean, it's not Shane's fault.
He must really love you.
He's doing what he thinks is right.
- What do you think is right?
- I trust him.
We're gonna cover our tracks
the best we can.
But if push comes to shove...
you gotta step up and tell the truth.
DA never gonna pursue the conviction
of a pregnant woman
trying to protect the father of her child.
It's not how Shane wants to do it.
He'll do it however you tell him to do it.
Is everything okay?
Sure.
Sweetheart, let me get that.
Hey.
Luminol.
Spray it all around. Use the light.
Blood traces will glow.
Here, I...
Fumes could be dangerous to the baby.
Cleanup is on you.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Sir, we caught that stalker lurking
behind the victim's house last night.
Good.
Just thought you'd like to know, sir.
- Captain.
- I need your signature.
- You ready for the monthly reports?
- Not yet.