Previously on "The Shield".
We keep hauling in
this many fish,
we might need to
find you new digs.
You're assigned to Trish
for the day.
I'll try to
break you in easy.
I have no problem
working with the Decoy Squad,
but we don't work
for them.
That's right.
You work for me.
I want my own child too.
With you.
A man like
Shane Vendrell
could get his woman pregnant
without even trying.
I will go to the doctor
and I will see what I can do.
We think this cuddler rapist
has been around for a while.
The victims could just pile up
until he makes a mistake.
So far,
he hasn't made one.
If you live
in the area,
keep your blinds drawn
at all times.
Because he scopes out
his victims during the day.
Your ex-wife and son
were found murdered.
I'm very sorry.
You hired someone
to knock over your house?
I have a coin collection
from my dad.
She got half
in the settlement.
So you hired someone
to steal them back.
It was
a one-time thing.
This guy came back for seconds,
killed them both.
Arnovic has given full
confession.
What's that gonna mean
for Tommy?
Probably his job.
We can't spend a nickel
until we know
which bills are marked.
Treasury's got Aceveda
checking bills
on any bust over a grand.
- List in Aceveda's safe.
- Just get the list.
- Got it.
- Go.
If we're looking for a body
it must be Lauren.
- You still got that boyfriend?
- Still got that wife?
No.
Still got that boyfriend?
- I can't do tonight.
- It's probably a sign.
- It's scheduling snafu.
- No, it feels like a sign.
Move. Go, boy!
Move!
- Here we go.
- Get him.
Get out of town.
- Blast right now.
- That's me.
Love you.
There you are. Get out.
- Damn it.
- Respect me, pal.
I love you too, baby.
All right, we're going again.
- Everything cool with Mara?
- Yeah, why?
I don't know. Seemed like she
was in a mood or something.
Shit.
Everything's fine.
Just that this first trimester's
like a 90-day PMS ride.
Yeah, or maybe she thinks you're
not taking it so seriously?
- We're getting married, aren't we?
- Set a date?
- No, not yet.
- What about a ring?
I bought her a Lexus. She can
wear that on her finger.
- She knows I love her.
- Yeah, dude.
But a ring lets her show the rest
of the world that you love her.
You getting your thing
waxed next week?
Man, come on. You gotta stop that.
Well, you gotta pony up for the rock.
- Yeah.
- Hey, it's me.
I need you down at the
storage unit ASAP.
- Where's Lem?
- He's with me.
- Is there a problem?
- Not on the phone.
Got here as quick as I could.
Figured we'd catch another case.
Who knew it'd be this soon?
- Maybe it's a sign.
- What's the situation here?
Actually, it's pretty quiet. Seems
to be a total lack of a situation.
The message said there was a
drug dealer working here.
Well, I may have over-exaggerated
the police nature of this call.
And I suppose you've got a key
to one of those rooms in there.
We've been dancing around each
other for a couple of years.
I'm just wondering what would
happen if we ran out of excuses.
- I'm on duty.
- I'm not.
- You got a pager if they need you.
- I've got a boyfriend.
- We already established that.
- It's really not a good idea.
You're right. You should get back.
What am I supposed to do with Koto?
Do you need to get that?
That's what voice mail's for.
That's the hello line.
Quiet!
Hello?
Hi, Mama. It's Toya.
Trish, you all right?
Nothing. Just chilling.
- I ain't gonna make it by for dinner.
- Can you say where you are?
I'm gonna kick it with
some friends tonight.
Holler at Walon for me, all right?
I love you too, Mama.
Trish is in trouble. Walon too.
- No more calls.
- Why? What's up, boo?
That white dude you hooked
us up with is a cop.
- No. No way.
- Undercover.
- Quit clowning.
- I just got confirmation.
Where you heard that?
What do you know about him?
Tips good. Drinks Scotch.
Shitty marriage. You know.
I thought we were coming
here to have some fun.
We could be in some shit.
- You included.
- Fifties can't do nothing.
- You ain't even done the whack yet.
- No, but I agreed to.
You'll stick with me till I can
get this shit taken care of.
All right.
Just let me check my face.
- Who is it?
- It's me. Open up.
What's going on?
There's money missing.
- How much?
- We're 7 G's short.
I was going through the stash,
getting rid of the marked bills.
Couldn't find a few.
So I did a count.
- We're missing 7000.
- Including some marked money.
- You sure you counted right?
- I triple-checked.
Somebody dip in...
- ...before shit hit the fan?
- I didn't take squat.
Don't even look at me.
If somebody did, speak
up now, it's forgiven.
Important thing is to figure out
where the money was spent...
...before Treasury gets a whiff.
I'm serious.
We're the only people who knew it was
here and the only people with a key.
Last chance.
Come on.
We've been a team
through all of this.
Now, who took it?
Trish was able to make the call, so
let's assume her cover's still intact.
- But Walon was made for sure.
- What's the emergency?
- Walon and Trish.
- Any idea where Trish was make a call?
No, we're tracing it. I'm gonna
need four units ready to roll.
Decoy Squad's been working undercover
on a murder-for-hire sting.
Farmtown Twelves been
doing contract hits...
...making them look like drive-bys.
Since when is the Decoy
Squad a gang detail?
Trish was our best way into the case.
Walon's supposed to drop
the money for the hit this afternoon
where we don't know.
But we've got to get him
before the Twelves do.
- You try his cell?
- He was worried he'd be searched.
Which raises the question
how this happened.
More important question is, how
are we getting our people back?
Claudette's got us on goddamn
janitor duty the last month...
...meanwhile Walon's out
hunting down banger trophies.
I didn't take that money.
Okay.
Think there's any chance
Tavon swung with it?
It's not enough you put
him on life support...
...now you gotta call him a thief?
Look, if he knew about the money,
he would've come to us for a piece.
Just so you know...
...I'm getting Mara
an engagement ring.
All right.
- Don't go hog-wild.
- I'm not. I'm going through Taylor.
You're using a fence to
buy your wife a ring?
He knows this guy who
sells them wholesale.
- It's on the level.
- Why not go to the jewellery mart?
Because Taylor's guy's cheaper
and I don't speak Farsi.
May I help you?
I just gotta get my
corn rows tightened.
What up, homegirl?
- Man, I'm straight with you.
- I need another favor.
Yeah, well, you're fresh
out of favors, One Time.
You're not hearing me
too well under there.
I can see why Pretty Boy
drops the cheese...
...to keep his female looking tight.
Think he'll keep her when he hears...
...she's been going out
with a Spooktown soldier?
Still sleeping with
the enemy, Desiree?
- No.
- Trick question.
We know you are.
I'm just trying to get my hair did.
I need to know who in the
Twelves is selling contract hits.
Pretty Boy don't talk
business with me.
Coo in his ear.
You got half an hour or
I start cooing in his.
- Hands where I can see them. Now.
- Hands up.
Let me see your hands.
Clear in the back.
- Storeroom clear.
- All clear.
- Canvass it.
- What's going on?
The Farmtown Twelve made a call
from this phone an hour ago.
- Where'd they go?
- Don't know.
What were they doing here?
- I let them use my office sometimes.
- Why?
Beats having them burn it down.
Desiree. Thirty seconds to spare.
I was just about to call Pretty Boy.
Let him know his number one
cooch was on the loose.
Kaliel Wilks. Street
name, Li'l Psych.
Any idea where we can find him?
Yeah, well, you work on Pretty Boy.
- He gives you anything, you call me.
- Right, I'm running it.
Got the address where
Walon's making the meet.
I got the name of their guy who
runs contract hits. Kaliel Wilks.
Got a reputation as
a bit of a psycho.
Ever hear of him?
No, but Shane's on it.
You have any idea how
their cover got blown?
Maybe they tailed Walon.
Walon might stink,
but he's not sloppy.
Rapist works in the area.
Delivering pizza, cable-TV guy,
meter reader, who knows.
So, he uses his job as camouflage
and scopes out his next victim?
Exactly. Thanks for coming
out on your own time.
I'm learning tons.
Still, gotta be raising
hell with your social life.
Please, I kicked my social
life to the curb last week.
This guy was seeing bought me
this tennis racket...
...so we could hit together, then he
insisted I leave it at his place.
Talk about control issues.
- Cop?
- No. Just some guy.
I play.
- Yeah, you any good?
- Yes. I am, actually.
Well, I'd say that we should hit
together sometime, but I'm lousy.
Probably bore you.
I'm not that good.
Think I want this goddamn ulcer?
- I didn't take that money.
- Nobody in here took anything.
- You gonna ask Shane about it?
- I'd bet on his loyalty...
...before I'd bet on
your math skills.
When we're done with this, I want you
to go back with Lem, count again.
Check the lock for tampering.
Got a picture of our homey.
Kaliel Wilks, a.k.a. Li'l Psych.
- What took so long?
- No rap sheet.
- Had his Marine Corps file.
- He's a jarhead?
Was. Duked it out with his CO,
they booted him. Section Eight.
Let's see how he feels with
our size 11s up his ass.
We've got 90 minutes until the meet.
Plainclothes has secured the area.
We'll roll out in 10
to take our positions.
ID'd our trigger boy.
- Combat-trained.
- Shit.
Make copies for everyone.
Once Walon's secure, I'll make
the call to scoop up the Twelves.
What if Trish isn't with them?
Haul them here.
Make them tell us where she is.
The captain and I will set
up in a surveillance van.
- How long's Trish been into this guy?
- He just popped up a few weeks ago.
Walon kept her on the sidelines
until he needed her.
She went to work at Polebusters,
got close to the Twelves.
Polebusters? She's
under as a stripper?
Cocktail waitress. She
cozied up to the bangers.
They bragged about their
murder-for-hire racket.
She introduced them to Walon.
And his murder they'll do for free.
Tell me what I have
to do to get back in.
You hired a thief to break into
your home, a thief that...
No jury's gonna believe
a murderer over a cop.
- Your sister-in-law corroborated him.
- My lawyer says it's hearsay.
DA's spinning it, so the
department has no choice...
...but to wash their hands.
I need you to talk to them.
- Tommy, you can't come back.
- It wasn't my fault.
I know you didn't mean for this to
happen. I can only imagine your pain.
I can't have you working here.
I'll do what I can so you
don't serve jail time.
Jail time?
You have to look out
for yourself now.
And you still have friends here.
Tommy?
What are you doing, man?
Aceveda's making me
clean out my locker.
Walon and Trish are missing?
Yeah, they fell off the
grid a few hours ago.
- Let me help.
- Tommy.
Just tell me what I can do.
Why don't you come to the
house this weekend...
- ...we'll watch De La Hoya?
- Sure.
What the hell is up with that guy?
Doesn't look like he's bird-watching.
- Hang on, pal.
- What's up?
Wanna tell me what
you're doing back here?
Just now?
Check the occupant.
- Turn around. Hands behind your back.
- I have permission.
- Hands behind your back.
- No...
Sorry to bother you, sir. We just apprehended
a man looking through your window.
Yo, girl.
It's all good. Dude with her.
What's wrong?
Honey, tell them to
take these off me.
- Do you know this man?
- Married to him long enough.
- He's your husband?
- I told you.
Look, No one's breaking the law
here officer.
- We're just...
- Playing.
Right. Role-playing
on the way to work.
With our friend.
Six hours out there, all we
get is a practicing cuckold.
See something like
that, you wonder...
...if we shouldn't stay
home, read the Bible.
Thanks, my partner already does that.
How you gonna solve this one?
You don't hope for another victim.
But the fact is...
...this guy hasn't made the mistake's
gonna get him caught yet. Sorry.
Yeah. Well, thanks a lot.
See any Twelves yet? Or Walon?
No, nothing yet.
Sit tight.
Farmtown crew coming in.
Any sign of Trish?
Negative.
Psych's not with them either.
I got Walon.
- Where?
- You should see him.
Shit. Trish isn't with him either.
- Pick up Walon.
- Give Trish a few more seconds.
They're gonna make him.
- Pick him up.
- I got it.
Cover's been blown.
Okay. Ready?
Let's move on these assholes.
Trish called the hello line.
It's a set-up.
- Where is she?
- Still missing.
- What do we know?
- Not much.
- Stop those guys.
- Nah, We're gonna shake them down...
- ... find out where Trish is.
- No.
Li'l Psych will make her
as blowin' the whistle..
Let these guys check in with him.
Walon says we should
let these guys go.
Keep Trish's cover intact.
Trish can take care of herself.
Pull them.
Shane, Ronnie, abort.
Abort.
I think I forgot my wallet.
Let them go.
What do you mean, he didn't show up?
Well, how'd he know not to show?
I got one more job to do.
I gotta grease that witness,
pick up a quick 10 grand.
Then we get the hell out of town.
Just sit tight.
What you got for me, daddy?
How do you say you met this cop?
I didn't know he was a cop. Why we
gotta keep talking about this, boo?
You know something, you
better spit it now.
He's just some white cat
that I met up in the club...
...wanted his business
partner killed.
Please stop.
Please?
- How long you known him?
- Few months.
If he's a cop, then
I'm in deep shit too.
I know.
I'll take care of both of us.
Yeah, I'll bet you will.
Here...
...sniff this.
Real power shit.
No.
I want a clear mind our first time.
We lost the Twelves in the subway.
Didn't you have
surveillance detail in place?
Well, the plan was to take everybody down.
You had us abort it.
Look, every available
unit is in on this.
- Who's shaking the trees?
- We're taking off right now.
Any idea how you got made?
Any idea?
- It's the mole.
- What mole?
The mole in the system,
the one I told you about.
Keeps warning the Twelves every time
a warrant or wiretap requests is put through.
- We never discussed a mole.
- IAD's tracking it for me.
- It's in my case notes last week.
- I didn't see that.
It's in the case notes. You
have people in the field...
...and no clue what they're doing?
Hey, easy. If there's a mole, it's not
Claudette's fault that you got made.
It is if she's submitting
wiretap requests for us.
- I sent one yesterday.
- Jesus.
All right, I'll call IAD and see if
they're zeroing in on this mole.
What else aren't you reading?
You and Trish's names were not used
in the request. I only used the case number.
- Her cover is still good.
- What if it's not?
I must have read this quickly. This
mole thing just didn't register.
I don't get her back in one
piece, I'll use every favor...
...I've banked for the last 14
years to get your lazy ass fired.
Come on.
Everyone seems to have heard of Li'l
Psych, but no one can locate him for us.
- What do you got?
- IAD's first look into the mole.
- They've only had the case a week.
- Oh, let me guess. They got shit.
Not exactly. They've narrowed it
down to court offices on Hoover.
- How many employees there?
- Twenty-six FTEs.
Give me five minutes with them,
I'll find your mole.
- What does five minutes entail?
- A shortcut you can live with.
I'll come with you.
- Ligature marks.
- Both strangled manually.
Time of death?
Off the top of my
head, four hours ago.
For Christ... I was
three blocks away then.
Landlord found them when he brought
the mail in. So, this one's her daughter.
Been looking after her mom
every day, apparently.
Goddamn it.
Always get this worked up
over a crime scene?
I've been after this guy
for a month and a half.
Now two people are dead because
I didn't catch him.
Presence of semen on the
older victim's abdomen.
The other victim wasn't raped obviously?
Have to wait for the
coroner's report.
Three blocks. Horseshit.
It's gotta be the Cuddler.
Daughter came home,
interrupted the rape.
Killed her, finished his business,
then murdered the older woman.
Never gotten this violent. What
makes you so sure it's your guy?
- It's him.
- Witness give you anything?
What witness?
Saw a man leaving the
building this morning.
Excuse me, ma'am. You saw someone
leaving this house earlier?
- About 8. I was walking my dog.
- Did you get a good look at him?
Well, he walked right past me.
I was picking up after
my dog at the time.
You know, not enough people
in this neighborhood do.
You hear anything about Li'l Psych,
you just buzz me pronto, all right?
These aren't stolen, right? I'm not
giving my fiancée stolen shit.
No. Look, it's on the
level, all right?
Hey, check this one out, right,...
...this brother caught
his fiancée bent over...
...pulling a train
with his groomsmen.
You can imagine his desire
to relieve himself of it.
I'm trying not to.
- What else you got?
- Okay.
That's a killer piece of ice.
What's the back-story?
Diamond guy I know had a
bad run at the race track.
So he unloaded a little
inventory on me below cost.
Yeah, it's beautiful.
Check out the four C's:
Cut, clarity, carats and colour.
Yeah, what about the fifth C, cost?
- Two grand.
What? Listen, you give a girl a rock like that,
she will get on all fours for you...
- ...and bark like a dog.
- She's my fiancée.
Two G's will keep her that way.
You got pounds of paperwork
coming at you every day.
Detective duty on top of that.
Anyone could've missed it.
Yeah.
Your real problem was going
with the Decoy Squad...
...and leaving your
starters on the bench.
The gangs are our thing.
- Okay, listen up.
- Attention, please.
Police. Everybody on your feet.
Let's go.
You, you, you.
You back there, and you two
in the corner. Come with me.
- What's this about?
- Police business. Keep typing.
I'm getting Judge Banks.
Faster than that.
- Where you from?
- Detroit.
- Santa Monica.
- Go sit down.
- You?
- Jersey City.
- Compton.
- You go, you stay.
- You?
- Leimert Park.
Inglewood.
- Where'd you go to school?
- Belmont.
- How about you?
- Wilson.
Oh, that's bad for you.
It's not in Compton.
- I moved to Farmington when I was 10.
- What block you live on?
Earl Street.
You two, split.
- You know any Farmtown Twelves?
- Who didn't?
- You been giving them a heads up of our warrant?
- No.
Sure you did. You gave up a wiretap
yesterday. You gave up a cop.
- No.
- Here comes the judge.
Listen, honey.
I'm gonna have the big boy here...
...crawl up your ass, find out
who you been hanging with.
How much you wanna bet he
finds gang ink on your taint?
Answer now or spend the next
eight to 10 wishing you had.
- Raheem Pyrums. Pretty Boy.
- What the hell is going on here?
Judge Banks. We need a warrant.
I'm gonna barely be able
to make rent this month.
But the look on Mara's face
will make it all worth it.
You think there's any
chance Vic took that money?
What?
He's getting a divorce,
a mortgage, rent.
Kid with special needs.
It's not like he hasn't
taken the money before.
Shut the hell up.
Who's Nancy?
Police. Open up.
Man, ease up on my door. That's real
oak, that ain't home-center shit.
- Hands against the wall, Pretty Boy.
- Desiree.
Spending a quiet day at home
with your man? Must be love.
Turn around, honey. Spread them.
Y'all go on and search.
Ain't nothing on me.
Sit your ass down, skid mark.
Looking for your boy Psych and
some bar skank he's hanging with.
- We ain't seen or spoke in weeks.
- Really?
I got a county clerk crying about
how she gave you and him...
...some police intel just yesterday.
Tell us where Li'l Psych and the woman
are, we'll forget we were here.
Y'all don't know nothing.
I know a few things.
Maybe a few that might surprise you.
You wanna know what I know, Chunk?
Just go on and tell them
where Psych at, Raheem.
You shut your face, girl.
Look, you said yourself he
was nothing but trouble.
Why you think they call him psycho?
Don't let that fool bring
the whole crew down.
- Call him up.
- Hell, no.
You know what, forget this. I
ain't messing with no fool.
And I damn sure ain't waiting
around for no jailbird neither.
Now, you call him or
I'm out the door.
A little rounder.
Yeah. Yeah, like that.
That's perfect.
Let's see.
- I thought you said you got a good look at him.
- Yeah, that's him.
This is an ear attached to a head.
It's a pretty good drawing.
Did he have a couple of eyes?
Maybe a nose and a mouth?
- Don't take that tone with me.
- This doesn't help us.
He walked by quickly.
And as I think I mentioned,
I was scooping poop at the time.
I just heard.
You okay?
Aceveda didn't lift a finger for me.
What am I gonna do? Work security?
Hey, we all end up there
in 20 years anyway.
Hey, Tommy. You got some pretty big stuff
hanging over your head right now.
Hey, you got him to
give you your job back.
Different situation.
You know what to say.
Maybe he'll listen to you.
All right.
- Oh, you don't wanna talk to him.
- No. Look, I will.
- You think this was my fault.
- No, I don't.
Look, you just name a night, Vanessa
and I will have you over for dinner.
We can talk about
where you should go from here.
Oh, you mean God's plan?
Yeah, thanks.
Appreciate it.
Gotta do this hit and get paid.
Let's go.
I don't know why you dragging me
in this Kaliel. I don't wanna see that.
You brought that cop in to buy a hit.
That makes you just as guilty.
Might as well be in on the shit.
Yeah?
Li'l Psych. Where you at?
I'm going to that job on Doyle Street.
- Already?
- I'm about 10 minutes out.
- You know the spot, right?
- 2130 Doyle. Why?
I'm just making sure you know.
You holler back when you
finished, I'll cash you out.
- What the hell are you doing?
- I got you an address, man.
If I told him to stop,
he'd have known something was up.
- Mark's in there?
- Ratted on a G, so his Christmas...
- ...is getting canceled.
- Look, boo, the cops are after us.
Maybe we should just
bounce on out of here.
I don't get my paper till
this snitch starts leaking.
It's on.
No. What the hell you doing?
Let go.
Vic.
What happened? Trish.
- Get an ambulance.
- Alright.
Can you talk?
Gray Monte Carlo. I got the plate.
- It says "To Nancy, Love Donald."
- Really?
I checked our computers. It was
reported stolen two weeks ago.
Yeah, that sounds about right.
I told you to get a
ring that wasn't hot.
Yeah, but.. but..
but you gave me the code.
- What code?
- Well, you winked.
- Like.. like this was on the hush-hush.
- I didn't wink.
- Yes, you did.
- No, I didn't.
How did you expect to get
a $10,000 rock for 2, huh?
Look, can you get me one
that's on the level or not?
Yeah, but it's gonna
cost you like 3 or 4.
Just get me a ring that I can use.
Okay.
Paul and Chris spotted the
license-plate number you gave us.
I had them hang on so
you could hook him up.
Thanks.
- At least your stuff was good.
- Let's go.
It's a relief that you're all right.
A little worse for the wear, but I
was never the Miss America type.
I had to do some coke
to keep my cover.
I'll put an injury on duty for you.
Do you need to see a doctor?
I should get checked out for STDs.
Get the morning-after pill.
Damn it.
Well, if you feel like you need
to talk to somebody...
I put a guy out of
the murder business.
I'm okay.
- I'm so sorry, Trish.
- That's cool.
Of course, that may
be the coke talking.
You ready?
Hey. I didn't expect
to see you so soon.
This is Hunter, my boyfriend.
Can we talk to you?
Sure.
Tell him what you told me.
Tell him.
What happened today was a mistake.
It can't happen again.
And?
I'm with Hunter. Don't call me.
Got that?
Elderly victim. Same geo-profile.
Apartment was visible from the street,
just like the others. It's gotta be him.
Lucas said they found
semen at the crime scene.
- I thought your guy didn't ejaculate.
- Maybe he found killing arousing.
This guy makes the first
killings of his life...
...and then spends the next
couple hours cuddling?
I thought the other rapes were in the
early evening. This was early morning.
Danny, you saw me put my
gun in my locker, right?
Yeah, I think so.
I can't find it.
I'll be right back.
Tommy? What are you doing?
Walk away.
Okay, Tommy, get out of the car.
- My lawyer says I should plead out.
- Look, man.
You don't have to do anything
you don't want do.
I'd get less than a year
in a prison.
We can make sure that
the truth comes out.
- Truth is I probably deserve more.
- You don't. Come on.
We can talk about this.
Look, man, you got people inside
who care about you. Julien, me.
- We know what you're going through.
- Yeah, I can see that.
Let me talk to Aceveda.
Okay. He's got pull.
He can use it if he wants to.
I can make him
change his mind.
- So now you'll talk to him?
- Yeah. I should have done it before.
Tommy, you still got family.
Let us help you.
Okay.
Get Aceveda.
Give me the gun.
Let's hear what Aceveda's
got to say first.
Okay.
All right, good.
Hey, officer in distress. Outside.
Officer in distress. Officer in dis...
- This way.
- Shot fired.
What's going on?
- Move, move.
- I got it.
- Right there, keep down.
- Somebody radio for a paramedic.
Radio for a paramedic.
Need help.
Alright. Come on, come on.
Let's go.
The department's providing
a counselor tonight.
You two can leave early to attend.
He was a coward.
He thought the job
was all that he had left.
Yeah, and we have to
clean up his mess again.
Session's at 8:00 at
the Fischman Center.
Thanks, I think I'll pass.
- So?
- We're 7 G's short.
Just like Ronnie said.
- And the lock?
- Not a scratch.
And besides, who's gonna steal seven
grand and leave a fortune behind?
So which one of us did it?
None of us did it.
Look, this whole Tommy thing's
got us all a little raw.
Ronnie reported the money missing.
Lem didn't even wanna steal
it in the first place.
So when you gonna talk to him?
- Day from hell, huh?
- Yeah, worst on record.
If they don't realize it yet, you're
the one who got them back safely.
I thought you were
talking about Tommy.
That too.
What about that murder-rape?
First it felt like the Cuddler,
but then I threw that out.
Your first instinct's pretty good.
What's your gut say?
The daughter showed up unexpectedly.
He killed her to keep from getting caught.
The murder excited him. So much
so that he finally orgasmed.
He gets off on murder?
But why would he cuddle
for hours afterwards?
Witness saw a man leaving the house
well after the time of death.
Maybe he left and came back.
Came back to the house.
Bodies hadn't been discovered.
See what he'd done.
Show the whole world
just how potent who he really is.
Sick.
It's plausible.
You gonna see that counselor?
There's something else
I've been putting off.
Listen, Julien, sometimes suicide puts
thoughts in people's heads, you know.
Why don't you go with me, see
what that guy has to say?
That's the last thing on my mind right
now. I'm in a much better place.
I've got Vanessa. Randall.
- We're gonna start our own family.
- All right.
Call me if you wanna talk.
Okay.
It's pretty late, sir. You've already
missed your last three appointments.
I'm a cop. My schedule's kind of
crazy. Can you just get me in now?
When you're done, place
the specimen here.
There are some visual
materials there if you like.
Okay.
Where is she?
Take it easy, man.
- Stay out of this.
- Hey, I'm with you.
Come here.
She belongs behind a desk.
Not messing with what we do on the
street. Doesn't mean anything.
- She's got Aceveda and the chief in her pocket.
- You think I give a shit about that?
And she's been playing both of us
against each other from the jump.
Now, if we start playing
ball together...
She can't command if
we don't let her.
Great minds think alike.
Do you need anything?
We're closing up in five minutes.
I'm fine.
- Yeah?
- It's me.
I'm sorry about before.
He caught me in a lie.
And he kept wanting more details.
- I just didn't wanna lie anymore.
- How are you?
I have some things I have to work out.
I've been with him for four years and...
I understand.
- Listen, don't do anything on my account.
- I know.
Sorry you got put in this position.
I'm not.
Okay.
You think you can buy me off?
Sit down.
- I'm cleaning.
- Will you... just sit down.
Come on, just sit down.
Playing my favorite song's
not gonna work either.
It's for the baby.
- What if it's a girl?
- Just open it.
It's incredible.
I've just been such a pain.
- It's just that being alone...
- Don't worry about it.
- And dealing with my mother...
- You're not your mother.
And I'm nothing like my father.
This thing's gonna work.
Baby.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
Vic?
Hey.
What's going on, man?
- Bad timing.
- No.
We are...
We just got engaged. Officially.
Look.
- That's nice.
- What's up, man?
It can wait.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
You celebrate.
Celebrate.
Hello?
Detective Wyms, sorry.
Can I help you?