Previously on "The Shield".
I'm supposed to be
captain in two days.
I still have some
unfinished business.
You are stealing my ideas,...
...and you're taking my job...
- ...and padding your résumé!
- I can still make a difference here.
- This is my job.
- Not yet.
They killed these Armenians
looking for our money-train cash.
There's four people who
know we took that money.
They're all sitting right here.
Stick to the plan.
Low profile. Business as usual.
- Hi, guys.
- We in your way?
- No, we're just...
- We're just finishing up.
Just needed to ask a
question and sneak a kiss.
Known this girl for two months,
you're buying a new car?
- It's preowned.
- Nice try.
No sale, you got it?
Why'd you say you'd help me?
- This is so embarrassing.
- I'm sorry.
I need to make a living. Would you
buy a half-million-dollar home...
...from somebody driving a '97 Neon?
The Byz Lats arming themselves
to the mother-tit with MP5s.
Well, the Byz Lats got their guns.
I'll disarm the Mexicans.
- Yeah, well, I used to trust that.
- Just give me tonight to prove it.
Who bought the guns for the Byz Lats?
An OG named Garza.
You got the guns?
Half of them. The Byz Lats
already have the other half.
I'm trying to put together a buy
while they're all in the same hands.
- I need some cash.
- How much?
- A hundred grand.
- Right.
Just to show them that we're real.
You have to file the
proper paperwork...
...and wait a couple of
days for the hundred grand.
Or you can stop by an ATM.
Jesus, between your
snoring and the phone...
- Yeah.
- Rise and shine, gorgeous.
- Time to go to work.
- Where are you?
About five feet from your door.
I guess we're up.
Hey, man.
Set up a meet with the Byz Lats. We're
getting those guns back tonight.
- Should I make some coffee?
- No. No time. Thanks, anyway.
I was asking him.
Don't worry about it. Go back to
sleep. I'll be home in a few hours.
Grab your gun, leave the badge.
We're not cops tonight.
We're neo-Nazis.
- Bye, baby.
- Bye.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
I see someone parked a new
Lexus in your parking spot.
Mara needed it for work,
and it's pre-owned.
And I told you not to buy it for her.
We're gonna talk about this later.
This Garza guy's just gonna
give us his guns? Why?
It's called commerce. Here,
you carry the money.
- Holy shit.
- Army-issue MP5s don't come cheap.
Aceveda signed off
on a wad like this?
Not exactly. Look, I didn't have time
to go through the proper channels.
- This is from our Money Train stash?
- For display purposes only.
Then it goes right back
where it came from.
I told Kern I'd get the guns back.
It's gonna make our
jobs easier and safer.
So you dipped into our life savings
to keep a promise to some scumbag?
Aceveda wouldn't sign off on time so
we're gonna do this off the books.
We won't even get credit for taking
these goddamn guns off the street.
We're gonna talk about
this later too.
Yeah.
You Garza?
You have a shipment of MP5s.
They belong to our organization.
Which is?
The Sword of the Creator.
If the gats are yours,
how come I got them?
We put down a deposit.
The dealer got nervous
and dumped them.
Half to your crew, other
half to the niggers.
Only the niggers got busted, which
leaves my eses with all the firepower.
Look, it's not your fault
our deal went sideways.
Which is why we're willing
to compensate you...
...rather than taking them from you.
Trust me, doing business with us
is preferable to doing battle.
We're still gonna need
somebody to mow our lawns...
...once this race war's over with.
Whatever you shelled out for
those guns, I'll pay double.
Look, you got two choices.
Either you put some
money in your pocket...
...or Elwood here dimes you the ATF.
I got a brother-in-law over there.
Ever have the feds crawl
up your ass before?
Half the money up front.
Then give me half the guns up front.
- Meet me in an hour.
- I pick the place.
And I want all 36 weapons.
Get him. I'll clear the car.
Let me see your hands.
You hurt?
He's dead.
One-Tango-4. Code 6. 1949, Coronado.
Two victims down. Request three units
and a supervisor for a crime scene.
- You guys set?
- We're good to go.
We got a four-runner.
Driver and a passenger.
Extra muscle in the back.
Two. They're strapped.
How'd I know this guy
was gonna bone us?
I got the guy in the hat.
All right, Fat boy's mine.
Any sign of the guns?
Yeah.
Okay, well, hang tight,
we're 10 minutes out.
Damn.
How many rounds went off here?
Multiple shooters?
- Who's that guy?
- Passenger in the back seat.
Bawling his eyes out
when we got here.
Hey.
Found this in the alley back there.
You don't need more than one
shooter if you're packing that.
Tell the two assholes
to drop their guns...
...and come out with their
hands where I can see them.
You been watching me, homes?
Actually, we gonna need the money and
the guns to help with our expansion.
Don't do something
goddamn stupid here.
Tell them to let him
go right now, asshole!
I lived five years longer
than I ever thought I would.
The vatos I came up with
in the game, they gone.
Go ahead, shoot. Make me a hero.
But Byz Lats are walking
away with that cash.
Your guy so much as twitches...
...my guy's gonna put one
in the back of your skull.
- Shoot the prick.
- No. Don't.
Ronnie, put it down.
Him first.
Ronnie, go on.
Mow your own lawns, putas.
Rough night?
Hey.
Sometimes mommy just won't nut
no matter how hard you hit it.
Shut up.
All right, here's the plan.
We're gonna set up
Garza in a drug sting.
Use the takedown to leverage
the guns off the Byz Lats.
- Who's Garza?
- Their soon-to-be ex-leader.
You get with your contacts.
I'll get with mine.
Let's find out who's dealing
quantity to this crew.
They're getting skunk
out of Humboldt.
I wanna get Garza on the hard stuff.
Tougher prison sentences
on the asshole.
You chase the rock, I'll find
out where he's getting H.
All right.
What about our goddamn money?
Our priorities are
guns off the street...
...and Garza rotting in jail,
knowing we put him there.
Our priorities? I don't
remember being consulted.
It's my fault for letting
a guy get behind me.
You never should've
been in that situation.
Shane's right.
What happened last night was an
error in judgment on my part.
We were out of position, outmanned.
It won't happen again.
In the meantime, we'll never
see that 100 grand again.
Yeah, that's on me too.
So stop whining and take
the money out of my share.
- Deal.
- No.
It's the cost of doing business, all
right? We should all take the hit.
Shane needs the dough.
He tell you...
...he bought the new squeeze a
sweet new ride? Against my orders?
On this job, you're the boss.
But when it comes to the Money
Train deal, we are partners.
I can live my life just fine.
Go ahead and live it. Count
your money and wash your Lexus.
We can get Garza and
the guns on our own.
News is the Byz Lats jacked
some white dudes buying guns.
-One bald head, one dirty crackerwood.
-Save it.
Three Byz Lats went down wet.
One of them's not getting
up on account of your guys.
I can't control every
dog in the pound.
They see the Byz Lats strapped
with goddamn MP5s. I mean, shit.
Your hollow points seem to be
getting the job done all right.
That was tooth for a tooth. My boys
gonna do desperate shit, they got to.
Talk about capping
Byz Lats kids next.
Well, you got to stop them.
Man, I can steer the ship,
but I can't turn it around.
I'm gonna get the MP5s.
And I'm gonna get this
Garza asshole good.
Ticktock.
I'm just here to let you know it's
about to jump off. Real spit.
Well, I'm here to tell you, any
more One-Niner drive-bys...
...I'm holding you
personally responsible.
The mayor's office and
tell them I need...
Chief Bankston, I've had trouble
getting you on the phone.
That's because I've been
ducking your calls, detective.
Am I wrong or was I not
offered the captain's job?
That was when the job was open.
Captain Aceveda has a plan for
cleaning up Farmington...
- ...and he wants to see it through.
- Yes, I know all about his plans.
If the promotion in Farmington doesn't
happen, put me someplace else.
Your value's at the Barn.
Besides, I don't have any
positions open anywhere else.
Be patient.
So you're telling me that a chief has
been outpoliticked by a captain?
When Aceveda takes office, do
I have your word I move up?
You have my support.
But you might try playing a little
politics yourself with him.
I thought you were working.
I got into something with Vic.
- You want me to make you a sandwich?
- No, I'm not hungry.
- What's the problem?
- Not important.
Well, it must be for you to
be all torqued up like this.
It's about me. Me and
this goddamn car.
Why does he even care?
It's not that.
Look, we can return the car.
I need it for work, but we
can figure something out.
No, we're keeping the car.
This thing between me and Vic...
...it's complicated, you know?
Sometimes brothers fight.
So why is he always making
you the little brother?
That's not how it is.
Dutch. Aceveda said you had
some questions for me?
Your missing guns.
They're MP5s, right?
- Yeah.
- It was an MP5 used in our shooting.
- Who were the vics?
- Two Latino bangers.
Sound like One-Niners?
No, we disarmed them.
- What's the neighbourhood?
- Coronado.
No, that's Byz Lats territory.
Don't worry. I'm on it.
Anything on Garza's cane slanger?
Got a description of a cat
driving a blue 740 on Lexanis.
Those rims alone, 2 grand a pop.
What'd the DMV kick out?
Got six of those
registered in Farmington.
Plate numbers.
Alonzo Wang.
My guy did say that the Byz Lats
heroin supplier is a black Asian.
So their heroin dealer's
also their crack dealer.
Makes it easy. Get me an address.
Everyone all right?
Yeah, fine. I just got
my new work schedule.
- And I thought we could go over it.
- Not now.
Okay. Know what? Take a look at it,
call me at home or the hospital then.
Which hospital?
I'm back at Mission Cross.
What, in the ER? That's
becoming a war zone down there.
- We respond to brawls twice a month.
- They have a high turnover rate.
That's how Heather was able to pull
some strings, get me my old job back.
You get two night shifts a week.
You hiring a nanny nights too?
- I thought you would take the kids.
- I can't...
I thought you wanted to
spend more time with them.
- I do, but...
- I spent 11 years...
...working around your schedule, Vic.
Divorce means occasionally
working around mine.
Hi, Corrine. Nice to see you.
Nice to see you too.
I gotta go. Call if
you have questions.
Thanks for this. I'll work it out.
Getting back together?
Not exactly.
Look, I got a tip.
Could put the Byz Lats'
supplier out of business.
- Yeah?
- I need a warrant.
How good's the probable cause?
- My Cl's got a stellar track record.
- I'll see what I can do.
This is time sensitive. How
long for the paperwork?
Depends how solid your paperwork is.
We could use this to pry something
loose on Dutch boy's case.
I got it, Vic. There's
a system in place.
Feed your warrant request through it.
Anything else?
Not at the moment.
Raymond Montes. He was the passenger?
Arrested a month ago for possession.
And this Calva guy.
Narcotics convictions, assault.
I can't even count the DUIs.
You, on the other hand,
graduated cum laude...
...National Merit winner... Me too.
Wasn't easy, was it?
So, what were you doing
with these two losers?
Raymond wasn't a loser.
He was my friend.
Since high school. He found out
these guys were beating on me...
...stealing my stuff.
High school can be hell.
Yeah.
Raymond made sure everybody
knew that if anybody hurt me...
...they'd get it back worse.
A guardian angel...
...with a rap sheet six pages long?
I don't know.
He just did what he did.
And now he's gone.
Sorry about your boyfriend.
Raymond's friends say you're
making threats against Garza.
You think he shot Raymond and Calva?
Come on.
Juan Pepe.
What's the question?
Calva was a Torruco, right?
So, what, Garza thought Raymond was
a traitor for hanging out with him?
You got the 411, why you sweating me?
All we're trying to do is catch
the killer of your boyfriend.
Garza marked Calva's ass for leaving
the Lats and joining the Torrucos.
What was Raymond doing with Calva?
Warning him.
Trying to get him to
come back to the crew.
Garza saw that as talking
with the enemy, retaliated.
You better get that puta before I do.
We'll certainly do our best.
- Where the hell is Tavon?
- He'll get here when he gets here.
If we hadn't gotten him involved,
we'd pop this asshole.
Use him to get our money back.
I'm trying to put this
prick Garza away.
I need a legal, solid case against
this guy to get him to cooperate.
If Aceveda's got so much juice, how
come he can't get us a warrant...
...while I'm still in my 30s?
He's on the move.
Damn it.
He's going back inside.
- Come on.
- Here's Tavon, let's go.
- We got the warrant.
- About time.
Don't blame me. Judge
had a Pilates class.
Can I help you?
Not only can you, you're going to.
Have a seat.
Clear!
Clear.
Check this out. My God.
Hey, boss.
I hope you got something for
a headache, because I'm it.
It's a regular Rite
Aid in here, Lonzo.
My lawyer's gonna read this warrant.
If there is even an
apostrophe missing...
You roll the dice on a 20-year
stretch. See how good we spell check.
Or you could get your ass
on the phone with Garza.
Tell him you got shipments of H and
coke you're selling at discounts.
Garza's late.
Yeah, our boy here says
he's never on time.
How long you gonna keep
Shane on the bench for?
He'll come back when he's ready.
Tavon, tell your girlfriend
to stop looking so nervous.
Relax, man.
Here we go. Game time.
That's our bag from last
night with our money.
Shit. That's not our guy.
It's not our guy.
It's Diagur, one of his lieutenants.
How are we gonna bust Garza
if he's not doing the deal?
Give him the drugs. You'll get
the money from him later.
- What?
- Just do it.
- What the hell...?
- Let this guy skate.
We take him down for the money
later on without Tavon around.
Tell him that your place
is under surveillance.
Hey.
Mind holding onto that for
a little while longer?
We got some heat on the crib.
Safer that way.
Right.
Besides, it's not like we
don't trust you folks.
All right. No problem.
Later, dog.
Yo. What the hell was that?
You're letting him leave with
the drugs and the money?
Vic? Vic.
I told you going to the
chief wouldn't help.
For the last 10 years,
Farmington has been the place...
...people come to buy their drugs,
sex, fence their stolen goods.
I wanna clean it up.
Spare me. I'm not one of your voters.
You had two years to clean it up.
And I'm finally in the
position to do it.
Anything else?
I need someone overseeing the
practical elements of my plan.
Your plan?
You would have command
over the Strike Team...
...and the new Decoy Squad.
- Think of it as a promotion.
- I had a promotion.
You took it away, remember?
Hands on the wheel!
Hands on the wheel now!
Get them up here.
- You again? What's your problem?
- I'm on a dope hunt.
Why don't you pop the trunk,
see if I bagged something?
- Damn.
- Where's Garza?
Garza, you're only 27, already CEO
of one of the biggest gangs in town.
You've taught yourself...
...what guys spend years in
business school trying to learn:
Leading men. Maximizing profits.
I decide to take the Lats
public, I'll let you know.
Let's talk about where you were
last night, midnight to 1.
Candi's Lounge. I got a VIP table.
Well, you're a very important person.
You like trim? Because
I can get you in.
Is that all?
Man, because I'm missing
an appointment.
Yeah. Relax.
The wheels of industry can turn
without you for a couple of hours.
You gonna take the fall for
your boss on these drugs?
That's exactly what's gonna happen...
...unless you tell me
where these guns are.
Man, I don't know nothing
about no drugs or no guns.
Come on, man, where do we find Garza?
No clue.
Look, I got nothing
against you personally.
But I had a beautiful plan
to take down Garza...
...and you stumbled right in my way.
How come we're not conversating
in a real cop house?
I take you in, you're in the system.
I lose control of the situation.
What happens to you gets decided
by some guy in a suit...
...who doesn't understand
how valuable you can be.
I'll never be valuable to you.
Sure you are.
You just need some convincing.
Esteban. We've got a
suspect in the shooting.
I need you to look at this lineup.
Take your time.
I told you. I didn't see anyone.
Sometimes, you think you
didn't see anything...
...then you see a face and
it all comes back to you.
No.
This group of guys in
my middle school...
...hated my guts.
Every day, they'd think
up something worse to do.
They'd spray-paint my locker...
...steal my homework, charge
me 10 bucks to get it back.
That was in the Midwest.
I can only imagine what
things are like here.
So I understand.
You gotta be pretty scared.
No one in this lineup
can see you, son.
I know you wanna do this.
For Raymond.
I didn't hear anything...
...I didn't see anything.
Okay.
We'll get there.
- He saw Garza do the shooting.
- Yep.
Kids growing up in this cesspool.
Finally meet one that's
on his way out...
...and he ends up in the back of
a banger car covered in blood.
You gotta ask yourself,
what's the point?
You okay?
Let me see your hands!
Don't fight us.
Give me your hands.
Sorry for the interruption.
- What the hell's he doing here?
- He's Kern. We like him.
Kern, meet the new
leader of the Byz Lats.
What are you talking about?
Garza's mi jefe.
Garza's out of a job.
He just doesn't know it yet.
I'm grooming you.
So you two are gonna draw some lines
and we're all gonna leave here happy.
You having a chronic moment, homes.
I ain't trucing with no spook.
Hold up. This taco boy
didn't call me no spook.
There's no need to go racial here.
No one wants to settle this...
...in a locked steel container
with our bare hands.
Right, Kern?
You two start talking this out. I'll
check on you in a couple hours.
Lem, you stay here.
Glad you're back.
You're the boss.
But my personal life stays personal.
You wanna tell me what that
little dance was about?
The dealer we were
supposed to take down...
...waltzes with the drugs,
money, and a stroll?
He's agreed to cooperate.
Now we're gonna set up Garza
and get those guns back.
I had to snag a goddamn
ride here with our snitch.
Lucky for you he drives a
Beemer with $2000 rims.
What are you doing?
Figuring out how much I've got
in savings and partial pension.
See if you can afford to quit.
- You're too young to quit.
- And I'm too old for this.
Aceveda's just trying to shore
up his cop credentials.
Couple of months, the numbers will
turn around, the job will be yours.
- I wish I had your faith.
- Hey.
You're the best cop
I've ever worked with.
Well, thank you.
Nobody else ever came close
to keeping up with me.
- Hold that thought.
- Do I have to?
Question, Vic.
Make it snappy, I'm
drowning in something.
Suspect in our shooting heads
up the Byz Lats. Name's Garza.
Wondered if you guys
have a profile on him.
Garza? That's the asshole
who's got our guns.
- We've been looking for him all day.
- I just cut him loose.
- He was here?
- Kid wouldn't ID him.
I know he did it. I need to
prove his alibi's bullshit.
Says he was at Candi's Lounge.
Yeah. Yeah, I may have
heard of that place.
Just happens to be on your way home?
Hey, we're all about the job.
Dutch, Crime Reconstruction called.
They're ready for us.
Thanks.
Garza goes down for
a murder charge...
...we won't have to prop up a shaky
drug bust with our own cash.
It goes back into its
hole, no questions asked.
Let's go knock down
this asshole's alibi.
You seeing what I'm seeing?
Literally rained bullets.
And not just into the front seat.
Okay, let's lose the art projects.
Are you kidding?
You know how many hours
I've been at this?
Take your pictures,
then tear it down.
First crime scene, son?
Hey.
Garza's alibi checks out.
He was at that club doing body shots
off some stripper named Poundcake.
- Titties for everybody.
- I didn't need to hear that.
Hey, Vic, that warrant check out?
The Byz Lats supplier?
Not a goddamn thing.
- I thought your intel was solid.
- The dealer's house was clear.
I had to pull Judge Davies
out of Pilates class...
...to expedite that warrant.
We're trying to connect Garza.
He's not the triggerman.
We know.
He is.
Sorry about this.
I gotta do this
witness-statement thing.
It's procedure.
No problem.
I talked to administration
at UC Santa Barbara.
They said you didn't
reenrol for next semester.
Move back to L.A.?
Hang out?
I guess.
- What are you planning on doing?
- How's it going?
Still at the friendly chat stage.
Dutch might go on all day.
- Applied anywhere?
- No. Not yet.
Is this gonna take much longer?
I'm sorry. Get up, walk around.
I know this room can feel
a little claustrophobic.
Come on. Would you just scare the
crap out of this shit already?
Think you can scare him
as much as Garza does?
- Actually, yeah.
- Let Dutch do his thing.
Okay, I know you
didn't see anything...
...the night that Raymond
and Calva were killed.
You sure you didn't hear anything?
No.
I told you. The music was
just bumping too loud.
- I couldn't hear any...
- Right.
- So how'd you hear the shots?
- What?
You must've heard the
first couple of shots...
...and hit the floor
pretty damn fast.
Otherwise, we're not
having this conversation.
Okay. Here we go.
You look at the crime-scene
reconstruction...
...it's amazing the
bullets missed you.
I mean, I know you're skinny, but...
Why am I even in this room?
You know why you're in this room.
- Think I had something to do with it?
- You did.
- Why would I kill my best friend?
- My partner and I did a little test.
From where the shooter was standing,
you can't see the passenger's seat.
- You only meant to kill Calva.
- I didn't even know Calva.
You wanted to come back to L.A.,
hang with Raymond, make money.
Best way to do that was
to join the Byz Lats.
Raymond wouldn't even let me join.
Which is why you went
behind his back.
Asked Garza to jump you in. Taking
out Calva was your initiation.
- No.
- You did the shooting.
You went down to the car
and you saw Raymond.
You know why he was
there, by the way?
He wanted to give Calva one
last chance to come back.
He didn't wanna see any bloodshed.
You were right about Raymond.
For a banger, he turned
out to be a good guy.
I didn't mean to do it.
- Who gave you the gun?
- It was an accident.
The gun that killed your best friend.
Garza did.
Can you help me? Please?
Not anymore.
It's still Esteban's
word against Garza's.
To convict we're gonna
need corroboration.
Well, I'm Mr. Corroboration.
Don't ask.
So how goes the peace process?
Middle East'll be a love-in before
these idiots sort their shit out.
What's the roadblock?
This fool ain't
offering me dxxx, man.
He ain't got nothing to deal.
We're the ones strapped.
See what I mean?
Hey.
I'm getting the feeling you're not
appreciating the promotion I gave you.
It doesn't matter to what I agree.
Garza calls the shots.
Garza's going to jail.
He's got his own guys
killing each other.
You ain't got nothing on him.
He already punked you once.
How smart was it sending a
19-year-old bookworm to do the hit?
A college boy gave him up.
You can't tell me
Garza's a business man.
I got his money, his drugs
and his top lieutenant.
You tell me one thing your
boss hasn't screwed up.
Your choices are climbing up the
ladder or going down the drain.
- lf the vato know I spun him...
- Who's gonna know?
This is between you and me.
I just need proof he ordered
the hit on this Calva guy...
...and the throne and the
crown are all yours.
Look, all I know is he
gave Esteban a gun...
...the address, and he printed
out a map how to get there.
That's all I know.
Good. Let's finish this thing.
- Knock it off! Now!
- Sir.
Sir.
- My appeal was at 11.
- Can you give us a minute?
- Where were you?
- It's been hectic.
Right. You promised that
you would be there for me.
Look, the vote's gonna be
2 to 1 in your favour.
I put in a call this morning.
It's a done deal.
I got my job back?
You'll get official word tomorrow.
- Thanks.
- You got it.
But I am really busy here, okay?
Okay. Sorry.
Thanks.
- Scared the hell out of him.
- What was I supposed to do?
You're in church on
Monday afternoon,...
...your life could use
a little excitement.
Guess what? They're bringing me back.
Really? Congratulations.
- That's great.
- They upheld your appeal? Wow.
Whose desk you have to bend over?
Sure as hell wasn't yours.
A guy can dream, can't he?
How's he working out?
- Doing good.
- Made a few arrests.
I thought I'd give you the news.
I'll talk to you later.
All right.
You better make sure your
people deliver on this truce.
- And if I don't?
- Hey.
You owe me. I'm keeping the
One-Niners from being wiped out.
We'll see. I mean, you got Garza,
but you still ain't got the guns.
No, but I'm smelling them.
Baseball cap's our
signal Garza's inside.
- Gave up his buddy?
- What separates them from us.
Loyalty, that most
disposable of virtues.
- Where's Garza?
- I got him. I got him. Don't move.
Hey!
He's going out the back.
Hurry up.
You have about two seconds to
tell me where the guns are.
Suck me hard, bitch.
We got him.
Hey.
Managed to stop him
before he got away.
Hey, captain, what's up?
The pastor from the church
lodged a complaint against you.
- Jesus.
- What's he saying?
Excessive force.
That's crap. The guy was
tweaking, he wouldn't go down.
Took four of us to
get him in the cage.
Tommy, give us a minute, please.
- Come on, captain.
- Tommy, please.
Fortunately, the pastor's a friend, so
I think the complaint will go away.
I just wanna make sure
you're all right.
Sir?
How would you characterize
the incident?
The amount of force was
necessary to affect the arrest.
And everything's okay with you?
Yes, sir. Everything's great.
Even if we don't get
him on the homicide...
...this should put him away
for a couple of decades.
Call me greedy, I still want
him for the murder-for-hire.
- Me too.
- Hey, Dutch boy.
Might wanna grab this
prick's computer.
See if there's anything
that ties him to Esteban.
Bag the laptop separately.
Where's my phone call?
We got your laptop.
Downloaded records of
your online activity.
The porn sites were illuminating.
I liked the map you
printed out for Esteban:
Directions from his house to Calva's.
I talked to the DA. You turn
in the remaining 35 MP5s...
...she's willing to take the
death penalty off the table.
Put the needle right here.
Show me where the goddamn phone is.
We'll get you a good
lawyer, all right?
- The guns?
- Look man, word's out you got popped.
Torrucos and One-Niners,
they coming at us hard.
Yo, homey, where those cuates at?
So we can protect what's ours.
Get a truck, pick up the guns.
Wait for my call.
And put a few aside for emergencies.
How we gonna explain how
we got this artillery?
We can't, so we won't.
Put this with the rest of
the Money Train stash.
It's 20 grand light.
Byz Lats' overhead, I guess.
Better than losing the whole hundred.
The way I figure it.
I guess everything worked out okay?
Got lucky.
So we cool?
Of course.
You got the Decoy Squad for sure?
They start next week.
Supposed to be great.
How'd you get Griggs to give them up?
He hasn't yet.
He's gonna call Councilman
Docknovitch to get me to back off.
Not knowing Docknovitch is
gonna need my support...
...on his zoning application.
Which you'll be only
too happy to give.
I think we need a series
of high-profile busts...
...using the Decoy Squad
to flush them out...
...and the Strike
Team to step on them.
In a very public way, you change
perception, you change reality.
Does this mean I can
welcome you aboard?
Anything I can do to help.
Shall I give Vic the good
news or do you want to?
- Shane's not home.
- I know.
I wanted to apologize for
barging in on you last night.
- No big deal.
- Look...
...you and I got off
on the wrong foot.
We should really get
to know each other.
- Why's that?
- Well...
...you're becoming a big
part of Shane's life.
Which makes you a
member of the family.
Never really been big on family.
Or cops really.
Shane's the exception.
Look, I'm just trying to find
a way for us to get along.
And I've seen that same smile
on about two dozen guys...
...who thought a wink and
a $3 gin and tonic...
...was all that it would take
to get me into bed with them.
I do something to piss you off?
I don't like the way you treat Shane.
But that's his problem.
You don't understand the world
that Shane and I live in.
Shane works for you, but
he comes home to me.
- You've known him for two months.
- I know enough.
I'm not sure what your problem is.
Maybe because you couldn't
hold on to your family...
...you're scared Shane's all you got.
- Excuse me?
- Whatever the reason...
...I got enough bullshit seeping into
my life without inviting yours in.
So please, don't pop in
if Shane's not here.
What?
I called Treasury to see if any of
these marked bills have shown up yet.
- And?
- No.
Whoever's got them is sitting on them
or spending them someplace safe.
I wouldn't sweat it. No one steals
money to sit on it their whole lives.
Sorry about that.
- Why?
- I know you had a connection.
Just when I thought he was a victim.
The minute I found out
he was a shooter...
...just another loser.
So you sticking around?
Can't retire on cat food.
Yeah, you'll never leave me.
Hey. Need some help?
No, I got it.
I was thinking, if we both talk
to Aceveda about teaming up...
...he might put us back together.
What?
You were my training officer,
but I'm not a rookie anymore.
Actually, I've been bumped back to P2.
So officially we're equals.
That's how it'd be.
Maybe.
But I like the way
things are for now.
Okay.
Glad things are working out for you.
I need to meet with you and your
guys in the briefing room...
...next Tuesday, 3:00.
Sure. What's up?
David's bringing in the
Decoy Squad from Wilshire.
They're gonna be working with you.
Great.
I'm gonna be in charge of both teams.
I'll fill you in on the
details on Tuesday.
Three o'clock.
- Just spoke to Claudette.
- Good.
Sounds like an
interesting experiment.
It's more than an experiment, Vic.
It's your assignment for
the foreseeable future.
I thought Claudette
was taking your job.
You'll have to stomach
me for a little longer.
How much longer? Just so
I can warn my stomach.
Maybe working under Claudette
will produce results.
I've been producing results.
Not today. You had a drug
warrant blow up in your face...
...Dutch and Claudette
beat you to a gang bust...
...those Army rifles you've
been so hell-bent...
...to get are still on the streets.
Doesn't seem like your finest hour.
I guess not.
All right, let me throw one in.
Bon voyage.