Last season on "The Shield".
- Hey!
- Who searched that guy?
- I did.
- Armadillo's death in the cage.
I got suspended for that. I paid
the price. You're firing me for it?
It makes it awfully hard
to defend this place...
...to the Chief when I
see crap like this.
Start acting like adults.
You gave that faggot
a blanket party...
...knowing full well you'd like to
be lying under the blanket with him.
Five across.
They're gonna have the most PC
useless force in the country.
Julien gets outted and
throws a xxxxx fit...
...and we take the fall for
some friendly ribbing?
You're running for office.
I'll leave you as Captain
until that run is over.
If you win you graduate
to City Council.
If you lose the primary
you resign quietly.
If you offered me that
job, I'd take it.
- So now you want it?
- No.
- But I'll take it.
- It's a save bet...
...that Aceveda will soon
be the first elected...
...Hispanic representative
on the Council...
- I thought he was gonna lose.
- He's supposed to.
- What does that mean?
- In six months from now,...
...he's gonna be our boss' boss.
You wanna rip off the Armenian mob?
- Right into our pockets.
- Where are we with the money train?
It's definitely pulling out tonight.
What about the guy who
ran the last site?
His name's Chorekian.
He's the advance man.
Follow him. Maybe he'll
take us to the new site.
You saw him hit me?
- I saw it.
- You be my witness?
For insurance.
Yeah, I guess I could do that.
I'm Armin Chorekian.
Cletis Van Damm.
Jesus Christ.
This is not good. Where is Vic?
Come on. We're gonna do this now.
- Get down right now!
- Get down!
What the hell happened here?
- We got dead bodies?
- I wasn't us.
They turned on each other.
One big hit, in and out,
we're set for good.
- Open up!
- She saw you, asshole!
- Goddamn peeping Tom.
- Open up!
- Put down the bats.
That prick saw my mother naked!
- Peeping into our bedroom window.
- He saw me! He saw...!
Drop the goddamn bats!
- What about him? He's the criminal.
- Hands behind your head.
There he is!
- I want them both locked up.
- He was jerking off!
He's a pervert!
How will I get off
on those saggy tits?
She shouldn't leave her blinds up?
You read me my rights.
- Lock them up.
- Could you shut him down?
Step inside, sir. Close the door.
- She's nothing to look at.
- Julien. Hey, Julien.
Am I working alone here?
- I saw you outside.
- Lock him up.
Dinky's having a slow morning.
We're killing a morning babysitting
a third-string dime bagger.
- Can't get much lower than this.
- Every bust's a good bust.
And one step closer to cashing
in on a small fortune.
Playing by the rules keeps
LA from our retirement fund.
Fill the chief's arrest quotas,
keeps our noses clean.
- Yeah, or in your case, brown.
- Shut up.
What's up, man?
Plus I get you two assholes
to keep me entertained.
I got you, man.
- Packing already?
- Just tidying up.
You and Claudette wanna
take a run at this.
- I'm already working two open cases.
- I'm sorry we're so short-handed.
I had some budget ideas about that.
If you give me access to personnel...
You're on detective duty
for a few more days.
So why don't you stick
to that for now?
Get down there. It's a double
homicide with special circumstances.
What special circumstances?
Someone forgot their fins.
Armenian immigrants.
Both had multiple arrests,
and both did prison time.
Post-mortem cuts.
One foot's a trophy.
Four's just plain weird.
They were dumped here. Killing
zone's somewhere else.
Given any thought to who you'll
bring on as my new partner?
Like the captain said,
I'm still a detective.
Three more days.
There's a Detective Ruiz
in Hollywood that's good.
Gabrielle Ruiz?
Gabrielle's quite a looker.
Is she?
No?
Wait.
Okay, run this, "4UOP21 1."
Hey, Ronnie, Tavon, you seeing this?
Yeah, we got them.
Looks like juveniles.
"R. Mark Lindman, MD."
I hope the doctor's kids
know some lawyer friends.
Bust it out!
- Here he comes.
- Shit. Hey, you.
- Give me your keys, here.
- Okay.
- Hey!
- Give me your keys.
Don't do it! Don't you...
- Go, go!
- Goddamn it.
Stay right here.
Get the kid!
Get your hands on the wheel.
- You're gonna lose him.
- Go. Get out of the way. Goddamn it!
Six-Paul-1 1, in pursuit of
a mid-'80s Monte Carlo...
...headed south on Water
towards Palm Heights.
We're losing him.
Chopper's got him. He's
not going anywhere.
Besides, we're staying out of trouble.
Let some other unit wreck their car.
Six-Paul-1 1, your suspect
ran a stop sign...
...is now traveling southbound at
a high speed along Cesar Chavez.
Three Monte Carlos turning
onto Chicago Street.
Look out. We got a C.A.
involving multiple vehicles.
This is Air-9 requesting R.A. to
the intersection of Cesar Chavez.
- Stop! Lem, handle this.
- Hey!
You all right? Are you all right?
Cut him off!
Stay down.
I got it.
I got him.
Yo, I need a knife.
The seatbelt's jammed.
Shit.
- Where's it coming from?
- I don't know. The van?
- Lem, get out of there!
- Almost got him.
Lem?
There's no one inside!
- You gonna take it easy?
- He's got a few burns. Mild shock.
He's in for a bigger one.
What happened here?
Car we were chasing
caused the smash-up.
The van swerved to
avoid it, caught fire.
Back was full of ammo.
- One hell of a fireworks show.
- Your chase caused this accident?
Felony pursuit, under control,
we followed regulations to a T.
Give me that report right away. I want
all my ducks in a row for downtown.
Hey, Dutch boy. I got a case for you.
Actually, I'm working
a double homicide.
Yeah? Well, I need a detective
to hand this off to...
...so I can get back to dealer duty.
Rodriguez might be back tonight.
How important is it?
I don't know yet.
All right, thanks anyway.
Hey. You know of any
internal Armenian mob beefs?
- Not offhand.
- How about off foot?
Found these guys this morning.
Harbor found two more last week.
Same shape.
Don't know them.
Looks like old-country
retribution though.
Somebody sure pissed off
the bosses back in...
Yerevan.
You're right.
Let me show these to my guys, see
if they recognize the stumps.
Great. Thanks.
They killed these Armenians
looking for our money-train cash.
They think it was an inside job.
What happens when they realize
it was an outside job?
There's four people who
know we took that money.
They're all sitting right here.
Stick to the plan.
Low profile. Business as usual.
- You pull our driver's sheet?
- Ain't got one.
He's an out-of-work cement mixer.
A van full of ammo, Jesse?
It is not against the
law to have bullets.
Well, it is if you drive
them across state lines.
You wanna tell me why you took a
Greyhound to Yuma, Arizona...
...picked up a van, filled it
with half a ton of 9 shells...
...and drove it all the
way back here to L.A.?
- Told not against the law.
- Who told you that?
Your son Diagur?
See, he's a player with the Byz Lats.
Is that who you're running ammo for?
He float his out-of-work
pop a day job?
Diagur is not in this.
There's no sign of a struggle
in either victims' apartment...
...but both their cars were
parked in their slots.
They went along willingly
with whoever killed them.
- Someone they were comfortable with.
- Armenian mobsters.
Anything more specific?
You remember Margos Dezirian?
The Jesus look-alike.
The Armenian drug guy who
killed a man in our cage?
- Then escaped the paddy wagon.
- You think he's involved?
It would explain the severed feet.
Margos is a big foot-fetish guy.
How do you know that?
In custody, the only words he said
were "delicious feet" to Danny.
I gave her a call.
She said he was constantly staring
at her feet like he was obsessed.
Well, it's not the only
lead we're chasing.
If I'm right, Dezirian's
back in town.
- I wanna bring in the feds.
- Based on a foot fetish?
If Dezirian's here, everybody wants
him. Us, Washington, Interpol.
Fine.
Hey, when I was talking to Danny,
she mentioned her final appeal...
...with the police
commission is tomorrow.
A good word from her boss,
future city councilman...
- ...might go a long way.
- I'm aware of the situation.
- You almost all packed up?
- What can I do for you?
One last favor before
you ride out of Dodge.
What's that?
It looks like one of the Latin gangs
is arming up for Armageddon...
...and I can't find a free
detective to look into it.
We're understaffed.
I got a vanload of ammo
driven by a Byz Lat dad.
- Where there's bullets, there's guns.
- Did the driver confess to guns?
It's gonna take some legwork
to prove I'm right.
In the meantime, I got actual murders,
armed robberies that take priority.
You're not interested
in preventing murders?
- Why don't you look into it?
- Fine.
Talk to the chief. Get him to back off
this arrest quota. I can't do both.
I can't get in whatever
arrangement the chief has.
- Can't?
- Won't.
More important things to worry
about than guns on the street?
I'll assign a detective
when one frees up.
Did you finish up the paperwork
on this morning's car accident?
Yeah.
- Lem.
- Yeah?
- You finish that accident report?
- Yeah.
- You said he wanted me to write that.
- He does. You done?
- Hi, guys.
- Hey.
- We in your way?
- No, we're just...
We're just finishing up.
Sorry to interrupt.
Just needed to ask a
question and sneak a kiss.
You buying a car?
Yes.
Yes, we are. I'm getting my
Realtor's license next week.
So I need a respectable
ride to show homes.
Really?
Yeah, I'm just helping out
with the down payment.
- He's the best.
- Yeah, the best.
So we're gonna meet
after work, right?
- Dream Motor Cars, off Sepulveda.
- Yeah, okay.
- Okay.
- I'll see you there.
- Bye.
- See you.
Bye-bye.
Go with Lem and Ronnie, keep
the dime-bag busts rolling.
Go.
Come on, lover. You and me
are ditching school today.
Interpol's dossier
on Margos Dezirian.
He's suspected of killing
three coca farmers in Chile.
All found with their
feet chopped off.
Let me see.
I need to run his known aliases...
...against international flight
manifests for the past month.
- He's in town.
- Detectives, you have visitors.
The two men you find
dead this morning.
I know who did it.
I see him waiting at my
home to kill me next.
My mother, my sister, her children.
If you protect us...
...I tell everything.
I know you, yes?
No, I don't think so.
Yes, you and your friend. Cletus.
The accident that day.
The guy paid up, I never had to call.
Right. Yeah, that's good.
Cletus?
I did not know you
work for the police.
Yeah, I was off duty.
I'm on duty now. I gotta
get back to work.
Known this girl for two months,
you're buying a new car?
It's preowned. I'm covering
the down payment...
...she'll take over when
she makes her first sale.
What happened to keeping a low
profile? Business as usual?
I'm using my own money, on my Visa.
Looks like you're buying a new Lexus.
It's preowned.
Being up to my eyeballs in
debt is business as usual.
Nice try.
No sale, you got it?
- Vic.
- What?
Dutch is interviewing
the guy that saw us.
- What guy?
- Armin. The advance man.
- What's he doing here?
- I don't know, but he recognized me.
- He remembered your name, Cletus.
- Cletus Vandamn?
You gave the alias you used to rent
the storage where we hid the money?
Well, it makes Lem laugh.
Hey, Lem, you gonna ride with
the A-team today or what?
You were following this guy
the day we stole the money.
- lf he starts stringing the facts...
- lf Dutch does. He heard.
That's it.
We move the money tonight.
New location. New name.
That is not the man
doing the killing.
Are you sure? His
name's Margos Dezirian.
That is Margos?
Yeah, I've heard of the name...
...but it is Lyor Slavok you want.
Lyor Slavok?
He is a soldier.
Who gives him orders,
Margos, someone else...
...I do not know.
It's all because of
this damn money train.
I heard a rumor a while ago about a
money train. Somebody ripped it off?
The Armenians are gonna keep dropping
bodies until they find out who.
Shit.
The latest quarterly
crime statistics.
Jumped up double digits in all areas.
Well, the best thing you can
do for us in city council...
...is to find the money to
fully staff this place.
I don't take office for
another six months.
I'm worried about right now.
You said you had a few ideas
about adding personnel?
The undercover Decoy
Squad working Wilshire.
Their original mandate was to
rotate among all districts.
Well, Captain Griggs has used his
Miracle Mile clout to hold on to them.
Well, that's why their numbers at
Wilshire look a lot rosier than ours.
The unit's had great success.
Well, Griggs will never give them up.
I was thinking of appealing
higher up the ladder.
To the chief?
You don't have anything to offer him.
It'll make you look naive.
What other ideas do you have?
Hey!
Strike a pose, boys.
You. Get out of here, man.
Get out of here.
I'm gonna go out on a limb.
Diagur?
- What, you psychic?
- Yeah.
I predicted your old man would
crash a vanload of ammo.
He's fine. It's you
he's worried about.
- Me too.
- Vic.
Those 9 shells aren't for
these little cap guns.
You guys expecting a new
shipment of hardware?
- Who's running this boy's club now?
- Yeah, we missed the last election.
You guys looking to shoot your way
back into business and territory?
Well, you know, we'll
do what we gotta do.
Really?
If I find out you're arming with
anything more serious than this...
...I will turn the Byz Lats
into my personal pinata.
Which means we shove candy up
your ass and beat you with a bat.
You pass it up the daisy chain.
Vic Mackey. My nigga.
Ain't seen you around
here in a while.
Yeah, we've been enjoying the sun.
New stuff?
Religious erotica.
Where in the Bible does Saint Schlong
visit our lady of the D-cup?
I'm giving the believers
what they want.
So, what's the news?
- Anyone selling guns to the Byz Lats?
- Nope...
...but I found out who's buying.
Yeah? Who?
You know the cat.
Lovely.
Let me see you spin around.
Nice.
- I might just...
- Hey.
Drama. Hey, ladies, ladies, ladies,
could y'all bounce for a minute?
Everybody, come on.
Sweet setup.
- Thought you were broke.
- Hey.
Slap, easy, man, easy. Easy, baby.
That's my boy, Slap. He got my back.
Whatever makes Slap happy.
- So who's financing this hot spot?
- You know. Found some investors.
Really? One-Niners buy a share?
Let's just say sometimes
you can go home again.
Come on. What's a gangster rapper like
you investing in heavy metal for?
We know you're making a
gun buy for your boys.
Well, you know wrong.
Really?
You know what?
We could make half our quota by
emptying the pockets in this room.
- Let's go. Hands on your heads.
- All right. Hold up.
Calm down, Hee-Haw. All right, man.
Yeah, I'm buying, okay?
But not because I want
to, because I got to.
The Byz Lats arming themselves
to the mother-tit with MP5s.
- Jesus Christ. Fully auto SMGs?
- Three dozen.
My boys just looking for
a balance of power.
- Byz Lats already have them?
- I don't know.
Same guy selling to me,
selling to them too.
Who's running this arms race?
He's regular Army.
- When's your buy?
- What about the Byz Lats?
They got it in their
greasy little heads...
...that south of Vermont
belongs to them.
I'll disarm the Mexicans.
And I'm supposed to believe that?
You forget last time we did business,
how you just shit all over me?
That was a onetime war
crime, and I apologized.
Now, what time's the buy and where?
You make me find out on my own,
you'll be facing a charge too.
- Detective Holland Wagenbach?
- Yeah.
Agent Quigley, U.S. Treasury.
- I asked for FBI.
- You got me.
I understand you have an Armenian
who wants to come clean.
Already has.
Who's the boss around here?
We've been concerned
with the Armenian mob...
...shipping U.S. currency overseas.
About four months ago, my office
instituted a sting operation.
What kind of sting operation?
In San Jose, the Armenians were
extorting a local businessman.
He allowed us to insert $50,000
of marked, traceable bills...
...into his payment to the Armenians
so we could track the loot.
See what banks were
washing the money.
- And?
- Not a single bill has popped up...
...in three months.
It's mystified us.
But then today, I was notified
by my counterpart in the FBI...
...that you were investigating
a robbery of the mob.
And four related murders.
We may have blown our
laundering case...
...but if any of these
marked bills show up...
...they might lead
you to your killers.
Someone inside?
Hey, I thought I heard
you guys in here.
Albert, Albert Kreeg.
I'm the manager.
Looks like you guys got
everything in okay.
- Yeah, we're all set, Al.
- Albert, like the prince.
- Yeah. We're good, Albert.
- Okay.
Okay.
Did you just move out a place?
- Yeah, I'm getting divorced.
- Yeah, I had a feeling.
Which one of the two of you is Mr.
London?
- That's me.
- Okay, I got those spare keys...
- ...that you asked for.
- Thank you.
All right then.
- Night.
Night.
Get new padlocks. I don't
want Prince Curious...
- ...having a key to this place.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Vic, we need you down here.
Someone slapped Slappy.
Well, the Byz Lats got their guns.
So much for passing this case off.
I don't think this guy is showing.
Where is he?
Guess he got spooked.
That's bullshit.
Your homeys are chilling
like it's happy hour.
- You thought I'd buy this pony show?
- You best just back up off me.
You're pissed off about
losing your boy.
How'd you feel if it was your boys?
Still doesn't give you
license to bend me over.
Look, he didn't show, okay?
Ain't my fault. He...
- Hey!
- Don't even think about it.
- He reached.
- I didn't reach.
- Get your hands out of your pockets.
Yo, just do it, son.
Vic, just take it easy, all right?
I'm telling you the truth, man.
When you get a new time and
place, you let us know.
I'll call you as soon
as I know something.
Straight.
All right, Vic.
Let's go.
I'll be waiting for your call.
Why don't you just calm down, man?
He's lying.
Why'd you say you'd help me?
This is so embarrassing.
I'm sorry. I want to help you, I do.
It's just I've talked
to some friends...
...this can add stress
to a new relationship.
- What friends? Vic?
- Come on, it's not like that.
I worked to get this
Realtor's license.
Yeah, I know that.
I need to make a living. Would you
buy a half-million-dollar home...
- ...from somebody driving a '97 Neon?
- From you? Sure.
Because your mother doesn't want
you bouncing off the walls.
- Mommy, can I have some ice cream?
- Come on.
Go. Put on your p.j.'s. Come on,
get dressed. Let's go, come on.
- No fair.
- Come on. Go.
- Hey, what's going on?
- Look.
And what's this?
Daddy and me.
That's great.
This is your favorite
part, right, Matt?
- Princess, go play with your sister.
- This is where the song ends, right?
Bye, song.
See you next time, okay, champ?
Bye.
Bye, Daddy.
I love you, Matt.
He's got a great energy.
That classical music
you were playing...?
It's the Tomatis Method.
Matt's learning to use his ears
as his source of hearing...
...so his other senses don't get
overwhelmed. He's responding well.
Yeah.
- Remember to do his drills with him.
- I will.
Mr. Mackey, it was nice to meet you.
- I'll just let myself out.
- Okay.
So I'll see you next time.
Told you he was amazing.
Matthew's actually talking.
We can have Owen two
more nights a week.
He has another job offer, but he wants
to work with Matthew full-time.
Things are kind of tight right now.
How much is it gonna cost?
An extra 300 a week.
Okay.
Look, I gotta get back to the job.
Book him.
I'll figure out how
I'm gonna cover it.
I only need for you to pay for half.
I'm gonna take care of the rest.
I'm going back to work.
There's a nursing shortage,
and the pay is good.
Full-time?
Thirty hours a week to start.
How's that gonna work with the kids?
I don't know, but we're gonna
have to figure it out...
...because it's something I wanna do.
Danny, hi.
Sir.
I'm temping here till my appeal.
How's that looking?
My lawyer says not
to get my hopes up.
I'm thinking of adding a few
more bodies to the Barn.
I'd be filling the slots with
people who can get with my program.
What program's that?
I need officers who I can trust.
Play tough but fair. Keep me
aware of anyone who isn't.
- You're looking for rats.
- No.
No, I don't want what happened
to you to happen to anyone else.
Just tell the truth if any
big lines get crossed.
- You mean by Vic.
- By anyone.
You interested?
You saying I can get my job back?
Think about it.
Give me your answer
when school gets out.
What?
Word is you're a little
unsure of yourself out there.
- Is that what my partner's saying?
- What do you say?
I'm doing just fine.
Look, Julien, I'm not the
one riding you here.
But you got a little problem
with respect in this house.
People are wondering what you're
doing about the beating you took.
Look, detectives haven't
made much progress.
Still can't prove who did it.
Everybody here knows who did it.
And they're watching you.
Where do we stand
with our triggerman?
We should have the
warrant within an hour.
- Good.
- Somebody say warrant?
Need me to knock any doors down?
Damn, I was gonna ask
her to the prom.
This warrant for that
Armenian double hit?
The mob's pissed about a
shitload of stolen money...
...that was ticketed
for the homeland.
They're whacking the
players to find it.
Armin was scared he
was gonna be next.
- Where's Armin now?
- Feds took him. Witness protection.
Good news is I finally got a
break on two unsolved murders...
...that have been screwing
up my perfect record.
How's that?
When this robbery went down,
two mob soldiers got killed.
Three, four guys in
masks came roaring in.
Took the cash, left the bodies.
- Hey, man, what's up?
- Armin told Dutch that the guys...
...who robbed the money train
killed those two Armenians.
- Hey, we didn't kill no one.
- Why the hell would he tell him that?
My guess, Armin knew those
guys were stealing from him.
Armin's the one who called the
shooter down there that night.
Scared enough to admit
money laundering...
...but not enough to admit
to his part in a 1 87.
So if the robbery leads back to us,
we're on the hook for a double murder?
Jesus.
Here are the keys to the new space.
With this new heat, we should
wait another six, nine months...
...before giving our cash
over to the real-estate guy.
- Nine months? You're kidding me.
- We've been sitting on...
I didn't mean to interrupt
your secret Klan meeting.
We left our hoods at
the dry cleaners.
Come on.
Every time I enter the
room y'all stop talking.
Maybe it's because we're
captivated by your winning smile.
- Yeah, or blinded by yours.
- Hey, you two done pissing?
Sit down. I'll tell
you what's going on.
The Byz Lats just opened
fire on our turf.
Aceveda doesn't have the
manpower to attack this...
...and Kern's not playing nice.
So we gotta do it
ourselves and do it fast.
We're gonna tap Kern's phone.
Find out when this buy is going down.
- What, you'll tap without a warrant?
- No time.
Not enough hard evidence.
You got a problem with
that, speak up now.
Two weeks ago, 1 2 cases of MP5s
were stolen from Fort Irwin.
Now, that's 72 guns on the
streets in the open market.
And I already picked up one body.
I don't want anymore.
Set up the tap on Kern.
Hey, look, it's the Village People.
Stand by, Vic.
- We're tapping.
- I don't believe you.
Jamir said all the skanks you hired
are light-skinned with fine bodies.
- What's up with that?
- Jamir's half-white.
- What do he know about fine bodies?
- I know you. Don't play...
Sounds like Kern's not too
big to be a little whipped.
Next thing, he'll be
buying her a new car.
- I ain't jumping on nothing.
- Don't cut me off, xxxxx.
- Let me know when the call comes in.
- Where you going?
Corrine asked me to pick
up Cassidy at school.
- Well, how long we staying here?
- Until the call comes in.
The conversation will
probably be in code.
Shit. I told Mara I'd
take her to lunch.
Four different guns. We'll
run them through Ballistics.
Look what the Dutch man found.
He mailed an international
package to Greece this morning.
- Look at the name of the recipient.
- "Marcus Dreliozis."
Sound like a Greek alias
of Margos Dezirian?
- Check out the comments section.
- "Contents contain dry ice."
I think we found our missing feet.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, I'll try.
All right, me too. Yeah, I
love you too. Okay, bye-bye.
Blow me.
Dude, we're rich.
- At least we're gonna be.
- Yeah.
- Just gotta ride things out.
- Yo, yo. Let me talk to Kern.
- You got him.
It's Lex. Guns are ready.
Get all the cash yet?
Yeah, man. I'm sitting on it.
- Be there in half an hour.
- Right here.
I think I just broke the code.
The gun boy just went inside.
There were six crates
and four Army pals.
- Four?
- Yeah.
We need backup.
Backup? Vic, we're here
on an illegal wiretap.
Six-Paul-1 1 requesting
additional units...
What are you doing?
- I'm getting these guns back.
- Vic, we don't have a warrant.
He's right. Maybe we should just
keep a low profile on this thing.
Roger, 6-Paul-1 1.
What's your location?
Hey, it's five on five.
You guys wanna go bullet-to-bullet
with three dozen SMGs?
I know what I'm doing.
Six-Paul-1 1, we're at the corner
of Fletcher and Riverside.
Roger that.
My client denies any
involvement in these killings.
We've got an informant in the
organization that implicates him.
This informant may have heard stories,
but he saw nothing with his own eyes.
What'd he mail to
Athens this morning?
- Books.
- In dry ice?
- This isn't even his name on this.
- He just said he sent it.
And the receipt was
found in his place.
The only question is, why were you
stupid enough to keep the receipt?
I'm not gonna ask him that.
Okay.
Why is he whispering? We don't
understand what he's saying anyway.
Margos Dezirian is gonna
be at this address...
...in Greece tomorrow, isn't he?
We're having the package
rerouted to us.
We'll see for ourselves.
Four of you, that way.
Go in the back. Take your cue from
those guys. Don't get in the way.
- Hands on your head!
- Hands on your head now!
Get on the ground!
Rabbit! Rabbit! Rabbit!
- Get your ass down, don't move.
- He ducked into a backroom.
- Don't twist my arm like that.
- Don't move.
- Kern, where's that lead to?
- Nowhere. The window's barred.
Hook these people up.
- Hook them up and get them out.
- Turn that off.
- Put your hands behind your back.
- Grab a gun.
Move, move, move it around.
Move it around.
- Get them out. Get them out.
- Yeah, I got them.
- Let's go.
- All right.
- Load them.
- Come on.
- Hey, man, I'm all...
- You inside.
It's your 800 rounds a
minute versus our 4000.
I'll give you three seconds to toss
that weapon or we're gonna open fire.
One...
...two...
Come on out.
These are the serial
numbers of the bills.
If they get spent, make their
way through the system,...
...they'll get flagged.
Maybe we can flag them earlier.
Money was stolen here.
It'll be spent here.
We should do cursory checks
on all big money busts.
Any luck siccing the
authorities on Margos?
Not yet.
I talked to somebody at
the American embassy.
Greek authorities
aren't gonna move...
...unless they hear from
somebody higher up.
You have connections in Washington?
I've been to a few parties.
I'm going, I'm going.
Taking guns from our soldiers,
selling them to gangbangers?
You must be very proud, asshole.
God bless America.
- Come here.
- Hey, we got it, man.
Hey, Vic.
You tell me. Who bought the
guns for the Byz Lats?
Yeah, like I'm just gonna admit
I sold guns to another crew.
Uncuff him.
What are you doing?
Instant court-martial.
The trained soldier grabbed my
spare gun and tried to run for it.
Guys.
Evidence. Right around there.
You either tell me who bought
the guns for the Byz Lats...
...or you and me are gonna
play some run and gun.
- Yeah.
- Then run.
You're out of your goddamn mind.
Run.
An OG named Garza.
He's king of the Lats.
That's a good little soldier boy.
You want Treasury's list or
you want me to hang on to it?
I'll keep it.
I saw you talking to Vic.
- Has he been asking about this case?
- I was asking him questions.
He has experience with
Armenian organized crime.
From here on, keep
him out of the loop.
Okay. Why?
- Because that's the way I'd like it.
- Detective, you've got a package.
Size 10 and a half.
Hold on.
Kern and his guys
were in on the sting.
They set it up. That's why
we didn't need a warrant.
That's right. Little always ready
to help his brothers in blue.
Give him to me, Julien.
Come on.
What the hell was that?
I thought you'd be a bit
more appreciative...
...since I just saved you
from a felony arms arrest.
- Call us even.
- Nothing's even.
One of your guys ain't dead.
Look, we gonna get different gats,
go see the Mexicans. It's on.
It's off.
My next stop is the Mexicans.
You have my word.
Yeah, well, I used to trust that.
You still can. Just give
me tonight to prove it.
You got tonight.
Y'all have a nice day.
What?
- Thought we were playing it tight.
- We are.
You put us all at risk without
letting us have a say.
Over guns we got nothing to do with.
And I'd do it again.
Well, I wouldn't.
I wouldn't.
I talked to my boss in D.C.
Here's the problem.
The Greeks don't wanna help us.
- They're a little pissed off.
- Why?
Because we make up reasons
for going to war.
- Act like the world's policeman.
- And missiles we sold to Turkey.
We're not the only
ones who want Margos.
Paraguay, Chile, Belgium...
It's not Brussels
asking to conduct this.
In a couple days we can go
through back channels...
We know where Margos
is gonna be tomorrow.
It's already tomorrow in Athens.
I just need a few
officers to pick him up.
He's wanted for murder
in four countries.
Can you get Lyor to tell
you where Margos is going?
No.
He's not talking.
Even in prison you need feet.
I'm sorry. I've done
everything I can.
Assistant Chief Phillips?
Claudette Wyms.
I remember, detective.
What's going on?
I think you should talk
to Captain Aceveda.
Why?
He's not stepping down yet, is he?
You should go talk to him.
I'm supposed to be
captain in two days.
I still have some
unfinished business.
How long?
- Until I take office.
- Six months?
It's a volatile time in Farmington.
I can't leave the Barn understaffed.
You're gonna bring in personnel?
- Yes.
- The undercover Decoy Squad?
- You're stealing my ideas.
I'm implementing them
along with my own.
You are stealing my ideas,
and you're taking my job...
- ...and padding your résumé!
- I can still make a difference here.
- I can make a difference.
- Not like me.
This is my job.
Not yet.
You're the reason for half the
problems in the first place.
Well, that's your opinion. And
I'd keep any others to myself.
I will not let you do this to me.
There's a bigger picture.
You're smart enough to see it.
The chief's not gonna help you.
He's gonna need me.
Army scab who sold the
Byz Lats their guns...
...says the buyer's name was Garza.
Garza? Thought he retired.
Well, maybe his pension ran
out, because he's back.
I need you to get in touch with him.
Tell him that you found a buyer...
...offering to pay
double what he paid.
That's all I got.
I'll cover you on the back end.
Hey, man, top's down pretty tight on
the Byzantine quarter these days.
That's at least a couple days' work.
You got two hours.
- Danny?
- No, no. I'll hold.
You got the guns?
Half of them. The Byz Lats
already have the other half.
I'm trying to put together a buy
while they're all in the same hands.
- I need some cash.
- How much?
- A hundred grand.
- Right.
Just to show them that we're real.
I just need it for a couple hours.
- Then put in a request with Central.
- I need it now. Tonight.
I'm not bending the rules for you.
Hey, look, I didn't
even want this case.
Then why did you take it on?
I'm the only one who gives a shit...
...about the damage these
guns are gonna do.
You're not. I've spent all
day calling in favors...
...to make sure things change in
Farmington in the next six months.
What's that mean?
You have to file the
proper paperwork...
...and wait a couple of
days for the hundred grand.
Or you can stop by an ATM.
The guy's wanted by Interpol.
I'm giving you the address. All
you have to do is pick him up.
What's so goddamn hard about that?
If my tone sounds superior...
...it's because I'm American
and you're Greek.
Trouble in Armenia?
Athens, actually.
What's going on?
Nothing. It's just
the usual bullshit.
Whom shall I fear?
You are the stronghold of my life.
Whom should l...?
Jesus Christ.
- What are you doing here?
- Confess...
- ...to what you did to me.
- What?
I just need to know.
Look, I just...
What the hell's your problem, man?
The truth... Just tell me the truth.
I didn't do anything to you.
Shit!
Say it!
Shit. God.
Though an army besiege me,
my heart will not fear.
Even though war breaks out
against me, even then...
Julien, please!
God.