Ohh, yeah!
♪ Powerpuff girls
fighting crime ♪
♪ To save the world
before bedtime ♪
♪ Here's the time to shine
when you're fighting crime ♪
♪ Power it up ♪
♪ Who's got the power? ♪
♪ We got the power ♪
♪ Breaking through the wall,
gonna do it all ♪
♪ We don't quit ♪
♪ Who's got the power? ♪
♪ We got the power ♪
Oh! Yeah!
Guys! You got to help me!
Aah! Aah! Aah!
They're after me! Aah!
Donny, what's the matter?
No time to explain.
Take only
what's important to you...
Like this used tissue
or this flashlight
or this second-place
macaroni sculpture.
Okay, Donny, deep breaths.
Just tell us who's after you.
Oh, nobody...
Just the most dangerous force
in all of Unicorn Land!
Donny, stop.
There's no reason to panic.
Except every reason!
Quick, start running in circles
and screaming.
♪
Well, whatever happened,
you're safe now.
You're with the Powerpuff Girls.
Whew. You're probably right.
I was worried
they followed me here,
but now I realize there's no way
they could possibly figure out
that I came here
to hide with my BFF, Bubbles,
at the only place I know
outside Unicorn Land.
I'm safe... probably forever.
Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah!
Sugar.
Spice.
Everything nice.
Wimp.
Target acquired.
Donny the unicorn,
prepare to be destroyed!
That's him!
He's the one
who's been chasing me!
Ooh, I like his jacket.
You know,
I said the exact same thing
when I first saw him,
and I got to tell you...
Hey, Robodork!
If you want Donny,
you're gonna have to
go through us.
That won't be a problem.
You can run, but you...
Good idea! Let's run!
Dog pile!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Ugh, what happened?
Where are we?
Bowling!
Donny, I didn't know
you could teleport.
Yeah, I can teleport
lots of places,
just as long
as they're bowling alleys.
I call the piggy ball!
Ooh, let me polish it up
with Mr. Used Tissue.
That's why it pays
to pack the essentials.
No bowling!
Way to run away, Blockhead!
Now the robot thinks
we're wusses.
Why you got to be
such a chicken?
I'm not a chicken.
I just have
chicken-like qualities.
Donny, it's time
to tell us what's going on.
All right.
But you better
go to the bathroom now...
I don't want to have to
stop my story in the middle.
Tell us already!
Okay, okay.
It all started
back in Unicorn Land.
♪ Unicorn Land ♪
My buds and I
were playing Frolic Ball.
Come on, people, let me see
some frolicking out there.
Oh, I got it!
♪ La, la, la,
la, la, la, la, I... ♪
Ooh.
Oh, no.
The ball went into the Ancient
Cursed Dark Forest of Darkness.
I'll get it!
All right, ball,
I'm gonna find you!
Nothin' gets past ol'
Hawkeye Donny the Hawk-A-Corn.
Aaah!
Hey! Ohh! Aah! Ohh!
Hey! Ow! Ohh! Ooh!
Ow! Ooh! Nng!
Come on. Ooh! Aah! Ohh!
More?!
Eee!
Ohh! Aah!
Aaaah!
Oof! Huh?
Hi, ball!
What?
The mirror glowed
with a ghostly energy.
A voice whispered from
the void, "Donny... Donny..."
Wait! I gots to potty.
Seriously?
Okay. I'm done.
So, there I was,
in front of the mirror.
It was calling to me.
This mirror clearly contains
a powerful force!
I knew what I had to do.
Aah! Gaah!
Blp-blp-blp, blp-blp-blp-blp!
Nice one, Donny.
But if you think that's good,
check this one out.
Gunh! Gaah!
Whoa!
Waah!
Huh?
Hi, there!
My name's Donny the unicorn.
At that moment,
I knew I was looking
at beings of pure evil.
So I did
what any brave soul would do.
Aaaaaaaaaah!
Get him!
And then that killer-corn thing
was like, "Pew! Pew! Pew!"
And I was like, "Aah! Aah! Aah!"
And you were like,
"Well, I don't know,"
and then, "Brrrnnn,"
and we're here!
Oh, Donny,
you did the brave thing...
by running away like a coward.
Seems like a trend with you.
We'll find a way to fix this.
And kick some butt
in the process.
Donny, as I speak,
my master is destroying
your home world
of Unicorn Land.
Surrender now...
and I shall
annihilate you quickly.
Hey, guys, how about we
check out the cool bowling alley
over in Citiesville?!
That's far, right?
And away we go!
Not this time, Wimpicorn!
Let's show that ro-butt
how we do things
on this side of the rainbow.
Don't worry, Don-Bon.
We got this.
And I'll get the snacks!
♪
Yeah! Go, Powerpuff Girls!
That's what I call
three strikes, you turkey.
Nice.
I cannot be stopped.
Oh, please. Spare me.
Wow! Wow!
Great job, you guys!
Oomf!
Now let's bowl
our troubles away!
Donny, he said his master
is going to destroy
Unicorn Land.
We got to help them!
Eh, I'm sure they'll be fine.
They got all that magic
and stuff.
I don't know, dude.
Sounds pretty serious.
What's serious is how
seriously funny this face is!
Glb-glb-glb-glb-glb!
Okay, that was pretty funny.
The time for joking is over.
Could you girls handle this?
I'm-a take a quick nap.
Not cool,
you walking night light!
Um, Donny?
You should probably hide.
Got it.
Okay, Donny, no need to panic.
Buttercup can totally handle
those things all by herself.
Hasta la pasta, Donny.
No one hurts my best friend!
Hi, Donny.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Unh!
Bubbles!
Nooooooooooo!
Your friend is very noble
but very much a dum-dum.
You are the only thing standing
in the way of my master's plan.
Prepare to be annihilated!
Aww, come on, dude.
Let's make a deal!
How about, um...?
How about...
you leave us alone
for this cool game token?
Or how about this bubble bath?
Or this red car
missing its wheels,
presumably on purpose.
How about a pot holder?
Or stock model mug?
Or this used tissue?
Or... or... or, um...
Adios, Donny.
Or... Or this second-place
macaroni trophy?!
♪
He is...
the chosen...
one...
Whoa!
He was a robot the whole time!
Donny, what... what happened?
Did you destroy the big baddie?
Yes? No?
Did you want me to?
Guys, we can celebrate later,
after we save Unicorn Land.
Psh, yeah.
W-We can't go to Unicorn Land.
Four more of those things
came out of that mirror!
Don't you remember
my excellent story?
But Don-Bon,
what about your friends
and your family?
My family?
We got to go.
Plus, I left my lunch
on the counter!
And it's string-cheese day!
Looks like the Powerpuff Girls
are going to...
Unicorn Land!
So... how do we get there?
I'll teleport us to the
bowling alley in Unicorn City!
Hang on!
Whoo!
We can totally get a game in
before we have to...
save Unicorn Land?
You know, there's something
different here,
but I can't really
put my hoof on it.
You think?
Freeze!
Man, this is just not my day.
Don't move!
Oh, no! This is it!
I never got to warn my mother
that Unicorn Land
is under attack!
Don't worry, Donny.
She already knows.
Hiya, Donny! Pbht!
M-Mom? Axel? Gretel?
We came to tell you
Unicorn Land is under attack!
Yeah, Donny.
We know. Now hurry.
Let's get you
to the U.A.C.B.R.H.Q.
before it's too late.
What's that stand for?
The Unicorn Coalition Alliance
Brigade Rebel Headquarters.
Oh, my gosh! It's so cute! Hurl.
Listen up, kids.
There's, like,
some for-real important stuff
you need to know.
Gretel has prepared
a visual presentation for us.
Pbht!
Donny, do you remember
the mirror you found earlier?
Yeah! I mean, kind of.
No.
That mirror is the infamous
Darkhorse Dark Magic Mirror
of Darkness,
into which the Four Unicorns
of the Apocalypse
were banished many years ago.
When Donny looked into it
and made one of his funny faces,
it broke the spell
and unleashed them
into the unicorn world
to spread their evil.
And now their leader, Stanicorn,
is harvesting the magic from all
the unicorns in Unicorn Land.
That's awful!
Once he absorbs
enough unicorn magic,
he will be powerful enough
to leave the unicorn world
and enslave other worlds, too...
Including yours, girls.
Man, Donny, you done goofed.
The only way to banish them
is by getting them
back into that mirror.
But it's deep in the fortress
being guarded 24/8.
"24/8"?
Yes.
Unicorn weeks have eight days.
Today's a Spursday,
so it's obviously the best day
to infiltrate their defense.
Donny, you must find the mirror
and make the same funny face
to send the four unicorns
back from whence they came.
Aw, why's it got to be me?
Because, Donny, you are...
the Chosen One!
What does that even mean?
I don't know! But it
sounds really cool!
I wish
I had more time to explain,
but we need to get you
in that fortress now.
You'll need disguises.
We're unicorns!
This is my nightmare.
And for you, Donny...
A beard? Hey-o-o-o!
Don't worry, dudes.
I'll be with you the whole time.
Now follow me! Unh!
Gretel, how many times
do I have to tell you
not to leave your jellybean
collection on the floor?
Bluhah-ruh!
Well, looks like
you're on your own, girls.
My magic can only get you
to the outside of the castle.
You'll have to find
your own way in.
Wait. What?
There's the fortress.
We just need
to get past the guards.
Get down!
♪ We are guards ♪
♪ This is a guard song ♪
Okay, guys, follow my lead.
♪ Guards, guards,
guards, guards ♪
Just play it cool
and act like
you know what you're doing.
Got it! ♪ We're guards, too ♪
♪ We're guards, too ♪
♪ This is a guard song ♪
Psst! Do you guys
know where the bathroom is?
Uh... yeah!
It's over there!
Hmm, actually, buddy,
I'm pretty sure it's over there.
Um, excuse me, I've been working
at this fortress for 50 years,
and I always go to the bathroom
right over there!
Well, I've been working here
for 51 years,
and I always
do my bathrooms over there!
Guys!
This place has only
been around for a few days!
Hey, she's right!
You don't work here at all!
Then neither do you!
Imposter! Imposter!
Oh, hey, guys!
Are we sure "the Chosen One"
doesn't mean "biggest screw-up"?
I'm sorry, guys.
I was just really getting into
my beardy character.
Ah-ta-ta-ta-ta!
Silence!
Allow us
to formally introduce ourselves.
We are the Four Unicorns
of the Apocalypse!
I am Joeicorn,
and my sword-wielding skills
have conquered
countless civilizations
throughout history.
I'm Petercorn,
and my thrashing guitar skills
have demolished entire planets!
Oww!
I'm Tanyacorn,
and I'm the girl one!
I am...
A short balding dude?
Aah! Hey!
Get a sense of humor, will you?
Humor?
I've never laughed at anything,
not once in my entire life!
Hmm!
Wow.
You must be
a real blast at parties.
I'm going to especially enjoy
taking my time to destroy
you four jerks
so... incredibly... hard.
Attention all Dark Unicorns
of the Apocalypse...
We are now serving tonight's
dinner of shepherd's pie,
followed by brownies a la mode.
That is all.
Oh, yum! Shepherd's pie!
I'll deal with you fools later.
Can't conquer the world
on an empty tummy.
Uh, aah!
We're gonna get zapped
into mush,
and everything is hopeless
because I'm a dum-dum!
And we're trapped
in here forever!
Hey! How'd you you do that?
Uh, supersonic punch,
stone walls...
You do the math.
Cool! Come on!
Let's go take down Stanicorn!
Right behind you, girls!
Soon enough,
I'll be at full power,
and I'll be unstoppable!
Frolic! Yeah, frolic!
Frolic! Frolic! Frolic!
Enough with the laughing
and frolicking!
Sorry, Boss.
Sorry, Boss. Sorry, Boss.
As I was saying, I'll be un...
Stop!
I won't let you
destroy Unicorn Land!
It's where I keep all my stuff!
Unicorns of the Apocalypse,
destroy them!
Donny, we'll take care
of the unicorns.
You get to the mirror. Okay!
Wait. Who does what again?
Snack on these
♪ Sweet riffs ♪
I'm gonna turn it up to 11!
Ha!
How about absolute zero?
What the...?
Oh, no! My baby!
Almost there!
You don't look so tough,
little girl.
Oh, yeah?
How about now, pony boy?
You think that's impressive?
Let's dance.
Let's get this over with.
That was my only horn,
you... sicko!
Aah! Cramp, cramp! Cramp, cramp!
Aaaah! Aaaah!
Aah! Aah!
Aww, you're so cute!
No, you're so cute!
No, you! You!
Bubbles! Oh. Sorry.
How's my hair?
Good job, girls! Where's Donny?
Whoo! High score!
Donny! Donny! Donny!
Oh, right, the mirror.
Go, Donny, go!
Go, Donny, go! Go, Donny, go!
I did it! I got to the mirror!
Make the face already! Make the face
already! Make the face already!
It's too late!
Aaah!
It's all over.
♪
What? Oh, no.
Donny! Donny! Donny!
What?
The reign of Stanicorn
has finally begun.
I'm unstoppable!
Donn-y-y-y-y!
What?
Girls?!
Oh, no!
I can't do this!
I failed everyone!
Donny...
Mom? Yes, Donny.
We're using
our bubblegum communicators
from the U.A.C.B.R.H.Q.
Pbht!
Donny, don't be scared.
You're the... Chosen One.
You never even told me
what that means!
What's the most special thing
about you, Donny?
That I'm terrible at everything?
No, Donny.
That you bring joy
to all those around you.
You bring happiness and laughter
to even the most humorless
of creatures.
You must save the world, Donny.
You're the only one who can.
How do I do that?
Oh, that's easy.
The trick is to... Mom!
Now there's no one
to protect you!
Uh-oh!
I'm so going to enjoy
stealing your unicorn magic.
I don't need my magic
to defeat you!
I'm the Chosen One!
Don't make me laugh!
That's exactly
what I'm gonna do!
Check out my funniest face
eve-r-r-r-r-r!
The... The face!
It's too funny!
Aah!
For demonstrating extreme
bravery in the face of evil,
it is with great pride
that I bestow upon you
the highest honor
in all of Unicorn land...
These prestigious
bejeweled trucker hats.
I'm so proud of you, Donny.
Aww, that is so sweet.
I can't believe Stanicorn
wanted to destroy these guys.
Our new leader
is so much smarter and cooler!
Pb-bht!
Yes, ma'am!
Yes, ma'am! Yes, ma'am!
Okay, guys, say cheese!
Mom! Check it out!
I'll show you the face
I made earlier!
Donny, no! Donny, no! Donny, no!