The frozen seas
are worlds unto themselves.
Beneath their ceiling of ice,
they have an eerie,
almost magical stillness,
cut off from the storms
that rage above.
in the winter, the feeble slanting
rays of the sun bring little warmth
and the temperature seldom rises
above minus 50 degrees Centigrade.
(H0WLiNG, WHiSTLiNG WiND )
For much of the year,
it is dark and cripplingly cold.
Yet, there iS life here
at B0TH ends of the earth -
the Arctic and the Antarctic.
For most animals, whether
they live in or out of water,
the winters,
when much of the sea is frozen,
bring the greatest challenge.
The northern hemisphere.
it's February,
and as the earth tilts on its axis,
the sun's rays
creep slowly northwards
and the Arctic emerges
from its harsh winter.
The Arctic is a frozen ocean
surrounded by continents,
and when the surface of the sea
between the continents
freezes from shore to shore,
land predators walk out onto it
to hunt.
it's early March,
and the sea is still covered
with ice...
But there are patches
of open water - polynyas -
that never freeze over.
Here, where tidal currents
are squeezed between islands,
the water movement is so strong
that ice cannot form.
Walruses spend the winter
in polynyas.
Here they have permanent access
to the air,
but they can also retreat
to the sea to shelter, to hunt.
0ther sea mammals overwinter
in polynyas as well - in this one,
a young bowhead whale.
Here, the current is really fast
and the shifting ice is dangerous.
This whale became trapped
when ice encircled it last autumn.
There is no food here,
but a whale must breathe,
and the only place it can do so
for miles around is in this tiny hole.
it's living entirely
on its reserves of fat,
but now, they're dangerously low.
it will be some months yet
before it can escape.
Elsewhere, other whales
have also been trapped.
These are belugas.
Their tiny hole in the ice
has been kept open not by currents,
but by the belugas'
continuous movements
as they rise to breathe.
0pen water is now
some 20 miles away.
it will be two months yet
before the ice melts.
The belugas are extremely thin
and most of them
are horribly scarred.
But their wounds
were not inflicted by the ice.
A whale would be a huge prize
for any meat-eating hunter,
and these belugas,
trapped by the ice,
are within reach of polar bears.
Well aware of the danger,
the belugas stay submerged
as long as they can,
but they can only hold their breath
for about 20 minutes.
Catching a four-metre-long whale
that weighs one tonne
is no easy task,
even if that whale
is weakened by starvation.
But a beluga
is well worth waiting for.
Day by day,
as the hole gets bigger,
it becomes increasingly difficult
for the bear to land a whale.
Keeping its fur in good condition
and free from salt
is important for warmth,
and the bear uses snow
like blotting paper.
These belugas have been attacked
by many bears
over the last six months,
and some have been caught.
it may have taken a long time
and a lot of patience,
but a catch when it's made
brings abundant rewards
of energy-rich blubber.
Gulls rely on bear kills
at this time of the year,
and the colour of blood
staining the ice
attracts them from a long way away.
The remaining belugas
still have a long wait
before they're released
from their prison
and the threat of slaughter.
Arctic foxes
also rely on the polar bears
to hunt on their behalf.
They're the jackals of the north,
and scavenge from bear kills
whenever they can.
in winter and early spring,
they're wholly dependent on bears.
0nly in the summer,
when the sea ice melts,
will they regularly catch prey
for themselves.
They're not strong enough
to tackle adult seals,
but can certainly take
new-born pups or birds.
This canny individual
is going to bury its prize.
it may need it
during the uncertain times ahead.
The presence of bears
affects the behaviour of almost all
the animals here, big and small.
The bears tend to avoid
the fringe of fragmented ice
bordering open water
where travelling
can be very laborious,
but that very fact
makes this area - the pack ice -
a particularly good place
for seals to pup.
Harp seals breed here.
Their pups are born with white coats
which camouflage them
very effectively against the snow.
Harp seals have
a very short nursing period -
a necessity
on this unstable pack ice -
but suckling is intensive.
The pup feeds for just 12 days
on milk that is 45 per cent fat.
Then it's abandoned
and has to fend for itself.
A male hooded seal.
This impressive nasal display
is used to warn away other males...
and to win a mate.
Hooded seals also breed
on pack ice.
Their pups suckle
for only four days,
the shortest nursing period
known for any mammal,
and all because
the threat of polar bears
caused them to breed
on the unstable ice.
Another Arctic seal opts
for the solid ice further north.
Because it's easy for bears
to hunt here,
these ringed seals
must be particularly vigilant
and have to hide their pups.
Ringed seals
are comparatively small,
so they can give birth
to their pups
in little caves or lairs
under the snow.
Here, a pup is out of sight
and protected from bad weather.
in late March and into April,
female bears emerge from
winter dens with their new cubs.
The mother has not eaten
for at least five months
and she's hungry - very hungry.
if she doesn't succeed in catching
a regular supply of seals,
her milk will fail
and her cub will die.
Bears have an extraordinarily
sensitive sense of smell
and can detect seal pups
hidden in the snow
from two kilometres away.
But a female ringed seal
uses several lairs
and a bear will have
to break into a number
before it finds one
that is occupied.
This is a crucial time for the cub.
By watching its mother hunt
and by copying her actions, it's
beginning to acquire the rudiments
of its own hunting skills.
Play is also important
for developing muscles
and improving co-ordination.
As the days go by,
the sun rises higher and remains
above the horizon even at night.
The female bear continues to hunt
until her cub is too tired
and can't keep up.
She's smelt something.
The pup escapes
through a hole in its lair
that leads to the sea below.
0nly one in 20 hunts is successful,
but this mother
must find a seal pup soon
if her cub is not
to starve to death.
As spring turns into summer, the sun's
heat begins to melt the sea ice.
Now, the ocean is accessible
and the Arctic's summer visitors
return.
Migrating birds
arrive from the south
to nest and feed on the seafood
now within their reach.
Brunnich's guillemots
are the northern equivalent
of penguins,
but they have retained
the power of flight
for they need to reach cliff ledges
where their nests will be safe
from predatory bears and foxes.
Nonetheless, they are as at home
in the water as in the air.
They dive down
to a depth of 50 metres or more
to catch fish.
in june, the ice begins to fracture.
The cracks - or leads -
form useful corridors of open water
for air-breathing animals.
Belugas, migrating
to their feeding grounds,
use these leads to penetrate
the ice-covered seas and reach areas
where their preferred food,
Arctic cod, has spent the winter.
The males regularly dive
to about 500 metres to find fish.
The females and young,
which have smaller lungs,
only go to about 350.
in late june and july,
narwhals arrive.
The females,
who usually lack tusks,
come first with their new calves.
The males follow a little later.
They also move up the leads
in search of fresh feeding grounds.
Bowheads. Up to 18 metres long
and weighing 100 tonnes.
These are the only large whales
that stay in the Arctic
all year round.
They are not after fish.
They're seeking smaller prey.
Despite having the largest mouths
in the animal kingdom -
the size of a small garage -
they eat tiny crustaceans -
copepods -
straining them from the water
with the four-metre-long strips
of baleen
that hang from their upper jaws.
in the summer,
they store enough energy
to last them
through the following winter
when food will be less abundant.
As the ice melts away,
the polar bears are forced
to head for land.
They are excellent swimmers,
and can cover 100 miles
of continuous open water if need be.
0ff east Greenland,
there is little ice left by August,
so walruses haul out
to rest on land.
At this time of year,
they are moulting,
getting rid of their old,
scarred, parasite-ridden skin.
A bathe in cold water brings
some relief from the itching...
but even there,
the odd scratch is irresistible.
They make daily excursions
out to deeper water.
Down at 20 metres,
they root around in the sediment,
using their sensitive bristles
to search out soft-shelled clams.
0nce they find a clam,
they suck its flesh from the shell
with their powerful,
muscular mouths.
Walruses can feed for
about five minutes at this depth
before they have to return
to the surface to breathe.
Elsewhere in the Arctic, belugas are
gathering in their thousands.
They congregate
in just a few large estuaries.
Belugas of all ages and sizes
come here.
There are even young calves.
Some are so young -
born only a week or so ago -
that they need help.
They swim on their mothers' backs
so that they can breathe
more easily.
As the tide moves up the estuary,
the belugas follow,
swimming into surprisingly
shallow water.
Like walruses,
they also need to moult.
A combination of warm fresh water
and vigorous rubbing
against the gravel does the trick.
They remain here for days
or even weeks,
so it's likely that socialising
is also important to them.
After moulting,
they head back out to sea to feed.
it's now autumn,
and the sea begins
to freeze over once again.
Thin sheets of ice form
at the surface
and pile up, layer upon layer,
gradually creating
an impenetrable barrier.
By late November, the Arctic ocean
is sealed once again by ice.
The lights of the aurora
play in the winter sky.
And at the other end
of the planet - in the Antarctic -
there is the southern aurora.
Antarctica is now
emerging from winter.
This is the coldest,
windiest place in the world.
Temperatures are still hovering
at a numbing minus 50,
and the returning sun
has virtually no warmth.
Very few animals can survive
such extreme conditions...
but Emperor penguins can.
(H0WLiNG, R0ARiNG WiND )
Standing on the frozen sea,
they endure the full force
of the Antarctic storms.
0nly by huddling together
can they survive
the appalling winter months.
They take it in turns
to bear the brunt of the gales.
They can only live here at all
because Antarctica is surrounded
by the great Southern 0cean
and no land predators
have been able to reach it,
so, unlike Arctic animals,
they're not threatened
by polar bears.
The sea is still frozen,
but one seal, nonetheless,
manages to stay here,
even throughout the winter -
the Weddell seal.
Underwater, it's protected
from the storms above,
but it must have access
to the air all year
in order to breathe.
And they keep
their breathing holes open
with their teeth.
0nly by continually
scraping away at the ice
can they maintain access
to the air,
but that means that their teeth
get badly worn down.
Then, they can no longer hunt
and eat effectively.
Weddell seals die young.
The continent of Antarctica
is so isolated and so high -
almost 5,000 metres in places -
that it's considerably colder
than the Arctic.
ice slides slowly down
from its centre
towards its rim
in immense glaciers.
During winter, the continent
effectively doubles in size
as the sea freezes over.
ice forms around its shores
and extends outwards
for hundreds of miles
around the entire land mass.
Under the sea ice live small
shrimp-like creatures - krill.
They have been here all winter.
During these dark months,
they feed by scraping algae
from the ice.
Remarkably, they also shrink in size
and revert to their juvenile form
to save energy.
As the temperature rises in spring,
the ice begins to melt,
and little air bubbles
trapped within it are released.
Microscopic algae grow
around these bubbles
and the krill now graze on them,
gathering them up
with their beating legs.
As the sun's rays grow stronger
and penetrate deeper
into the water,
floating algae begin to flourish,
and krill leave the dwindling ice
and gather in swarms
as they harvest this new crop.
Far to the north,
beyond the blanket of sea ice,
chinstrap penguins
have been overwintering
in the open ocean.
The occasional iceberg
gives them the chance of a rest -
if they can get onto it.
But at this time of year,
where they really want to be
is on land.
it's just getting there
that's tricky.
it's spring, and the penguins
are returning to breed.
Their need to get ashore
is now urgent and imperative.
Doing so is all a matter of timing,
and picking the right wave.
But their journey
has only just begun.
Most of them will have to walk
many miles
before they can find a nest site.
(TREMEND0US DiN)
This is Zavodovski island,
which has the largest
penguin colony in the world.
About two million chinstraps
breed here,
and they come to THiS island
for a good reason.
it's an active volcano.
The heat from the crater
and the fumeroles
keeps the slopes
free from the ice and snow,
allowing these chinstraps
to start breeding earlier
than those further south.
But then again,
living on an active volcano
is not without its risks.
Unlike the Emperors,
these penguins are able to lay
their eggs on the bare ground.
Little wonder so many choose
to brave the mountainous waves
in order to get here.
Further south, near the continent,
the blanket of sea ice
is beginning to break up.
icebergs are gigantic fragments
of ice
that have broken away into the sea
from the front of glaciers.
During the winter,
they were frozen into the sea ice,
but now they're set adrift
once more.
As the bergs break up,
they form brash ice.
it litters the backwaters
of the Antarctic peninsula.
Minke whales make their way
into these placid waters in summer.
This is the most abundant whale
in the Southern 0cean.
Minkes are one of the smallest
of all the baleen whales,
and like all others,
they come here to feed.
The majestic humpback whales
are also summer visitors.
They have travelled
thousands of miles
from their winter breeding grounds
in the tropics
to gather the food that becomes
available here in summer.
in just four months,
they accumulate enough fat
to provide them with energy for
the whole of the rest of the year.
All these animals have come here
in search of one thing -
the krill.
Krill is the mainstay
of the Antarctic food web.
it occurs in phenomenal quantity -
billions of individuals
in a single swarm,
and swarms can stretch for miles.
Fur seals also collect
this rich, super-abundant food.
Krill swarms are very patchy,
but once found,
feeding is easy.
Humpbacks engulf
hundreds of thousands of them
in a single gargantuan mouthful.
When the going is good,
the whales feed continuously,
each eating
up to two tonnes of krill
in 24 hours.
Further south, near the continent,
the sea ice is still sound.
Here, where the ice remains
for most of the summer,
Emperor penguins make their home.
These have been feeding out at sea,
and are now ready to make
their way back to the colony
to feed their chicks.
instead of heading
straight for the ice edge,
the penguins hesitate
some distance from it.
They're nervous.
They dive down
and investigate the ice edge...
And for good reason.
Leopard seals patrol this border.
Leopard seals are the Antarctic's
equivalent of polar bears.
They're the top predators,
but they hunt most successfully
in the water,
so by and large,
the animals they prey on
are safer out on the ice.
They have a lazy grace
that belies their ferocious nature.
Confident that the coast is clear,
the Emperor penguins
head for the ice...
but they certainly don't linger.
Now they have a long walk back
to the colony.
Emperor penguin colonies are
some way back from the ice edge.
in winter, they may be
as much as 100 miles from it,
but as the summer progresses
and the ice melts,
the edge comes ever closer
to the colony.
So by the time the chicks
are fledged
and ready to take their first swim,
the water is close by.
This colony is in the lee
of a headland,
and that prevents the ice
from being broken up
by ocean currents.
The returning adults
are so full of food
that they can barely walk,
but with no predator
to threaten them now,
they can take their time.
Somehow, in this melee
of 60,000 or so penguins,
a parent has to find its chick.
it returns to the place
where it last left its chick
in the hope
that it might still be close by...
but chicks tend to wander,
so the adult has to call to it.
(ADULT MAKES L0W TRiLLiNG CALL)
(CHiCK MAKES HiGH-PiTCHED PEEP)
The chick responds,
and they slowly
home in on one another.
The plaintive entreaties
of the chick
stimulates the adult
to regurgitate a mouthful of fish.
With the return of one parent,
the other is free to go to sea
to feed for itself.
Aware of the leopard seal's
presence,
the penguins press together
at the ice edge
unwilling to be the first
to risk diving in.
0ccasionally,
the seal comes out onto the ice
and attempts to grab one...
But its most successful strategy
by far
is to lie in wait.
it hides behind a corner of ice.
The Emperors gain confidence
and make a dash for it.
The first wave of penguins escape.
0nce in open water,
they will be safe.
But the seal is alerted
by the noise,
and through the mass of bubbles,
it makes its attack.
Almost invariably, it makes a kill.
Encouraged by the absence
of the seal,
the remaining penguins
make a break for the open sea.
in time, their chicks will fledge,
and when the Antarctic autumn
is near its end,
these adults will walk
across the newly-formed ice
to endure yet another winter
on the frozen sea.