0ver 60 per cent of our planet
is covered by ocean
more than a mile deep.
That, the deep sea,
is by far the largest habitat
on Earth
and it's largely unknown.
join us on a journey
to the very bottom of the deep sea,
to an alien world
never revealed before.
it's home to some
of the strangest animals on Earth.
Fish flash in the darkness.
New species are discovered
on almost every dive.
More people have travelled
into space
than have ventured this deep.
Come on a journey
into the abyss.
A sperm whale takes a breath,
its last for over an hour.
it's about to leave
the warm, well-lit surface waters
and dive far down
into the cold, dark depths
of the deep ocean.
At the surface
it took in air at the same pressure
as we breath it.
But it's going to look for food
at more than 1,000 metres down,
where pressure is 100 times
that on the surface,
crushing the whale's lungs
to just one per cent
of their volume.
For us to follow the whale,
we need the very latest submersible.
A reinforced acrylic sphere
with walls 12 centimetres thick
protects a pilot and our cameraman
from the enormous pressure below,
and allows the submarine to dive
to just over 900 metres.
(PILOT) 900 feet,
With every passing metre,
pressure increases
and sunlight diminishes.
(PILOT) 1,000 feet,
By 300 metres,
it's already very dark
and the temperature of the water
is dropping fast.
We are entering the twilight zone,
a weird world of gloom
where many animals have become
completely transparent.
in this twilight,
and animal needs to see,
and yet, as far as possible,
must avoid being seen.
A giant amphipod,
12 centimetres long
and almost perfectly transparent.
its head is completely filled
by two huge eyes
with which it strains
to detect its prey.
Another twilight monster, phronima,
the inspiration
for the Alien movies.
She and her developing
pink offspring
live like parasites
in the stolen body of a jelly.
This impressive cutlery set
and its huge eyes
make phronima a powerful predator.
Even really complex animals
have become transparent
in the twilight zone.
Squids are among
the most advanced of invertebrates,
but this one never meets
a hard surface in its entire life,
so its body need not be as robust
as that of its shallow water cousins.
There's a rich variety of jellies
that live nowhere else
but in the deep sea.
Thousands of tiny cilia propel them
through a world without walls.
invisible in the gloom,
they grope blindly for their prey.
Comb jellies let out long sticky
nets to catch passing copepods.
But the most extensive death trap
is set by siphonophores.
This pulsating bell
is the head of a colonial jelly
that can be 40 metres long.
Millions of tiny stinging cells
drifting through the sea.
500 metres down,
and in even
the clearest tropical waters
only the faintest vestige
of the sunlight remains -
so little that our eyes
can't detect it, but others can.
Survival in the twilight zone
is all about seeing,
yet not being seen.
Hatchet fish
are masters of the game
of hide and seek.
They have the large, sensitive eyes
needed for seeking prey
but their bodies are flat...
and their sides are highly silvered.
Head on, they are just visible,
thin though they are,
but as soon as they turn,
their mirrored sides
reflect the remnants of blue light
from the surface,
and they disappear into the gloom.
Viewed from the side,
whole shoals can hide in this way,
but what about from below?
The tubular eyes
of many of the predators,
even in this gloom,
are able to distinguish their prey
silhouetted against the faint
glimmer of light from above.
Hatchet fish, however,
have a way of confusing any eyes
that might be searching for them
from below.
Their bellies carry rows
of light-producing cells
called photophores.
They can use these
to exactly match the changing colour
of light from the surface far above.
This counter shading
breaks up their silhouette,
making them almost invisible
from below...
almost.
But these are no ordinary eyes.
The enormous yellow lenses
enable their owner to distinguish
between light produced
by photophores and sunlight.
So, one device for escape
is countered by another
equally subtle one for attack
in an evolutionary arms race that
has been waged for millions of years.
Descend below 1,000 metres,
and you enter the dark zone.
No sunlight whatsoever
penetrates this deep.
The temperature of the water
is below four degrees Centigrade.
The pressure is more than 100 times
that at the surface.
Life becomes ever more sparse.
it's a dark, dangerous world.
Relative to body size,
these are the largest teeth
in the ocean.
They are so big
that their owner
can't close its mouth.
They belong to the fang tooth.
Unlike most deep sea fish,
this has powerful muscles
and is an aggressive hunter.
With food in such short supply
at this depth,
dark zone predators have to be able
to deal with a meal of any size.
Many animals here are dark red,
like this deep sea jelly.
Caught in the lights
of the submersible,
it's a spectacular firework display
of colour.
Normally, no red light
penetrates as deep as this,
so animals with red pigment
appear completely black down here,
perfectly concealed.
Predators here, however,
don't just rely on vision -
many have tiny eyes.
instead, their thin, rod-like bodies
are lined with organs sensitive
to tiny movements in the water.
This monster, half a metre across,
is a hairy angler.
This is the first time
it's been seen.
it's covered with hundreds
of sensitive antennae,
which detect the movements
of any prey careless enough
to stray too close
to this motionless predator.
But this, surely,
must be the strangest of all
the deep sea fish yet discovered.
A highly sensitive metre-long tail
hangs down from the head
that makes up a quarter of its body.
its eyes are tiny,
but its mouth is truly enormous.
it's called the gulper eel
because it can engulf a meal
of almost any size.
Hanging motionless in mid-water,
its enormous gape enables it
to deal with passing prey,
whether it's small,
or large.
Gulper eels can swallow prey
as big as themselves,
which is very useful in a world
where you never know
when the next meal is coming along.
Even in the dark zone,
there is S0ME light.
Turn off the submersible headlights,
and you see a pyrotechnic display
outside.
These lights are created by animals.
This is bioluminescence.
A deep sea angler fish
flashes in the darkness.
The light is generated by bacteria
that live permanently
inside the lure
which attracts prey
to these murderous teeth.
There are all sorts of lures
out in the darkness.
Come into my mouth, little fish!
And what is the purpose
of THiS lure,
suspended on a long rod,
way below its owner's
terrifying set of teeth?
it's difficult to be sure,
but then, this monster does have
another giant flashing lure
much closer to its mouth.
These fish are called anglers
because they use their lures
in much the same way
as fly fishermen
use their imitation flies.
For a hunting squid with huge eyes
this glimmer is intriguing.
it might just be food.
A satisfying meal
for a fish
with a highly extendible stomach.
Attracting a mate
in this endless darkness
can be even harder
than finding food.
Flashing lures may be helpful;
certainly, only female anglers
have them.
The tiny males are just a tenth
the size of the females.
Their only purpose is somehow
to find a mate in the darkness.
She releases chemicals
into the water
which the males scent with a special
white organ in front of their eyes.
Having found a partner,
the male bites at her belly
with specially designed teeth.
He needs to get
permanently attached.
Within a matter of weeks,
the male is completely fused
to the female,
and there he will stay
for the rest of his life.
Her blood circulating in his body
provides him
with all the sustenance he needs.
in return, she gets a continuous,
reliable supply of sperm -
a brilliant solution to the problem
of finding a mate
in the vast emptiness
of the deep sea.
To help in the constant battle
between predators and prey,
some fish in the dark zone
have developed headlights.
These light-producing photophores
beneath their eyes
may be used to search out prey
in the darkness.
Most bioluminescence in the deep sea
is blue or greenish-blue,
but a very few predatory fish
produce red light.
With this,
red prey becomes obvious
in the darkness.
Red light is rare down here
and most animal eyes can't see it.
0nly these fish can do so.
This gives them a sniper scope -
a headlight invisible
to their targets.
This copepod, unalarmed,
takes no avoiding action.
Bioluminescence
is useful in escape
as well as attack.
A shrimp senses a threat.
it spins in the water,
releasing a bioluminescent glue.
This acts like a burglar alarm,
startling the attacking fish
and leaving it illuminated
in the dark,
and vulnerable to its own predators.
These twinkling lights
in the darkness
are produced by copepods.
They probably flash like this
to communicate with one another
and confuse their predators.
The most sensitive eyes in the ocean
belong to an ostracod
called gigantocypris.
it's the size of a pea,
but that's enormous
for an ostracod.
Copepods are a favourite prey,
and it actively searches
for their flashes in the darkness...
but this copepod has a way of
confusing a hunting gigantocypris.
it discharges a packet
of bioluminescent liquid.
The flash is delayed,
like a depth charge.
Spinning, confused, in the water,
gigantocypris chases
after the flashes...
and the copepod
slips away unseen
into the darkness.
The ultimate bioluminescent
defence mechanism
has to be the light show
created by the deep sea jellyfish,
periphylla.
That, presumably, is the way
it scares away its enemies.
These bright lights
are all produced by firefly squid.
Normally, they live way down
at around 300 metres,
beyond the reach of
these japanese fishermen's nets...
but for a few months each spring,
they come to the surface each night.
The brightest lights
come from the bioluminescent tips
of their two front tentacles,
but it's only in the dark
of the deep sea,
that you can really appreciate
the full complexity of their displays.
it's not just their tentacles
but their whole bodies
that are covered in photophores.
The exact function is not clear.
The bright tentacle tips
may be for attracting mates
or dazzling predators.
The rest may be camouflage,
providing counter shading
for the squid
as they journey up
into the twilight zone.
Every night in the season,
hundreds of thousands of squid
journey up into the shallow water
to spawn.
Before dawn,
they will return to the depths,
leaving their eggs
to develop in the shallows.
The daily cycle of the sun
has a profound influence on life
in the deep ocean.
As the sun sets,
it triggers the largest migration
of living organisms on our planet.
0ne thousand million tonnes
of animals
travel up from the dark zone
into richer, shallower water
every night.
Tiny grazers are first up,
searching for the microscopic plants
that only grow
in shallow, sunlit waters.
Predators follow the grazers.
An enormous variety
of different animals
join the convoy
or feed off it as it passes.
Many will travel up hundreds
of metres towards the surface,
and, at dawn, finding themselves
at risk from predators,
the visitors return
to the safer darkness of the depths.
The sun's rays
only have a direct effect
in the top 100 metres
or so of the ocean.
it's only here that photosynthesis
can take place
and coral reefs can flourish.
Leave this thin, rich slice of life
and travel over the outer face
of the reef
and you quickly enter
a far more demanding world.
Below 150 metres,
photosynthesis becomes impossible.
You find no plants,
just animals.
Here, the animals are adapted
to catch marine snow -
particles of dead animals and plants
that drift down from above.
So they depend second-hand
on the energy captured from the sun
by organisms in the surface waters.
Travelling close to the sea floor,
we're going to take a journey
to the very bottom
of the deep sea...
to a world completely separate
from the mid-water above.
At around 300 metres,
the drop-off levels out, and we move
out onto the continental slope.
This stretches for about 150 miles
from the coast,
sloping in a gentle gradient,
down to a maximum depth
of 4,000 metres.
Water temperatures down here
drop below four degrees Centigrade
and the pressure can reach
up to 400 times that of the surface.
Without the lights
of the submersible,
it would be completely dark.
The water is crystal clear because
there's so little organic matter.
0nly three per cent of any food
in the surface waters
reaches the continental slope.
At first sight,
it appears a lifeless desert,
but take a closer look
and you notice a network
of tracks and trails.
There is life even down here.
These animals would die immediately
if brought to the surface in nets,
so you can only see them
behaving normally
from submersibles.
Many are new to science.
The deep sea floor is dominated
by echinoderms -
sea cucumbers, brittle stars
and sea urchins.
There are literally millions
of them,
marching across the sea bed,
hoovering up any edible particles
in the sediment.
They come in all shapes and sizes,
and though they are thinly spread,
these are among
the most numerous animals
on the planet.
Their spikes are good
for locomotion and defence,
but perhaps not quite so good
when it comes to mating.
Finding a mate
in this largely empty sea floor
could be a problem,
so some urchins
stay together in herds
to be sure that they're never
too far from a potential partner.
Rocky outcrops
provide good anchorage
for animals that rely on food
that might drift past.
These crinoids or sea lilies
look like plants,
but are, in fact, animals.
Their long stalks ensure that
their umbrella of feeding tentacles
are positioned to best effect
in the current.
Particles are swept onto the arms,
and carried down to a mouth
in the middle of the umbrella.
These sudden movements swat away
tiny amphipods that try to steal
the sea lily's captures.
Coral reefs are not supposed
to exist in total darkness,
but recently, a new kind of coral
was found as deep as 2,000 metres.
in the cold waters
of a Norwegian fjord,
there was a deep sea reef
30 metres high and 200 metres long.
This coral gets no energy from
the sun, so it has to be very efficient
in catching food.
its polyps are far larger
than those of shallow water corals.
These are, in fact,
the largest coral polyps
in the ocean.
They belong
to the deep sea mushroom coral.
Their three-centimetre-long
tentacles
can catch far larger prey
than other corals can.
This necessity to capture
every particle of food
that comes within reach
in this near desert
has radically changed many animals.
Most tunicates
are filter feeders,
but this one has become a predator
and its greatly enlarged siphon
has been converted into a trap.
Most sea cucumbers
stay firmly on the bottom,
but not this extraordinary
deep sea species.
its skirts of skin
allow it to swim hundreds of metres
above the sea floor.
Eventually, it will descend
and, with luck,
will land on fresh feeding grounds.
This has to be the most
extraordinary animal design of all.
it's a polychaete worm
and, normally, you would expect
the long, pulsating body
to be stick firmly in the sediment.
This worm,
alone in its group,
swims in the open water.
Propelling itself
with its yellow frill,
it moves about
and so finds new sources of food,
or maybe succeeds
in escaping from a predator.
This is chimaera,
a close relative of the sharks,
less than a metre long.
Sensory pits on its chin
help it hunt prey on the bottom,
while its surprisingly large eyes
may help it spot bioluminescence.
Large fish are rare down here -
there's not enough live prey
to sustain them.
Most have become scavengers.
A dead tuna has attracted
a deep sea conger eel...
and a six-gilled shark.
These monsters grow
to eight metres long.
Six gills are living fossils.
For 150 million years,
they've existed unchanged,
living in water
as deep as 2,500 metres.
Very few people have glimpsed
these sharks from submersibles,
and we know almost nothing
about their behaviour.
The body of a tuna
is a substantial meal,
but just occasionally,
a really gigantic corpse
drifts down to the deep sea floor.
This is the freshly dead carcass
of a 30-tonne grey whale.
it's resting on the sea floor
a mile down.
it's only been on the bottom
for six weeks,
but already it has attracted
hundreds of hagfish.
These ancient scavengers
are nearly always the first
to discover a fallen body,
and are attracted from miles around.
They lack jaws and rasp at the flesh
with two rows of horny teeth
on either side
of their sucker-like mouths.
Next to arrive,
a sleeper shark -
a real deep sea specialist.
They grow to over seven metres long,
and have never been filmed
at such a depth before.
The gaping wounds
in the whale's flank are its work.
Unlike the hagfish,
it has powerful jaws,
so is able to rip off
huge chunks of meat.
Sharks, hagfish
and a whole succession
of different deep sea scavengers
will feast on the carcass for years
before all its nutriment is gone.
Eighteen months later,
when we returned to this whale,
all that was left was
a perfect skeleton stripped bare.
it was almost
as if a museum specimen
had been carefully laid out
on the sea floor.
At first, the skeleton
seemed totally abandoned,
but even after so long, there was
still some flesh left in the head.
Hagfish have a skeleton
of cartilage and are so flexible
that they tie themselves into knots
and so get a better purchase
on the flesh they feed on.
But smaller organisms had fed here.
A thick band of white bacteria
had formed on the mud
outlining the original shape
of the whale,
and on the skeleton itself,
colonies of specialised bacteria
were extracting energy
from the bones themselves.
Most remarkably,
and in huge abundance,
polychaete worms were collecting
the last edible fragments.
These are a new species
that so far have only been found
on the fallen bodies of whales.
Scientists have discovered
178 different animals
on a single whale vertebra,
most of which have been found
nowhere else.
This whale, lying over a mile down,
was not filmed from a submersible
with an acrylic sphere.
Such craft can't go as deep as this.
To withstand the pressure here,
you need a far stronger submersible.
This is Alvin,
a two-metre-wide sphere
with just enough room in it
for a pilot and two observers.
its walls are made of titanium.
The viewing ports have to be tiny -
any larger,
and the submersible would implode
under the enormous pressure
down here.
Alvin can dive
to 4,500 metres,
three miles below the surface.
Around 3,000 metres, the continental
slope finally flattens out
and joins the abyssal plain.
This covers over half
the earth's surface.
Mostly it's completely flat,
but in places
it's gashed by massive trenches
hundreds of miles wide.
The deepest of these
is the Mariana Trench,
which drops to over seven miles
below sea level.
There are just five manned
submersibles world-wide
that can reach the abyssal plain,
and between them so far,
they have explored
less than one per cent of it.
There are a thousand times
fewer large animals down here
than on the continental slope,
but in places,
hundreds of brittle stars
cross the sea bed in search of food.
Fish have been found right down to
the bottom of the deepest trenches.
Most come from one family -
the aptly named rattails.
They forage near the sea floor
and use their battery
of sensory pits
to follow odour trails
from rotting carcasses.
Rattails can travel long distances
across the abyssal plain
in search of food,
but others down here
prefer to sit and wait.
This is a tripod fish.
it supports itself
on two specially adapted fin rays
and can sit motionless
for hour after hour.
it does have tiny eyes,
but it's almost totally blind.
it locates potential prey
with a pair of fins behind its head
which are sensitive
to even tiny movements.
We know more about the surface
of the moon
than we do about the abyssal plain.
Every dive still produces
complete surprises.
This deep sea octopus
is about the size of a beach ball
and has been nicknamed Dumbo.
An umbrella of skin
between its tentacles
and its extraordinary flapping ears
allow Dumbo to hover effortlessly
over the sea floor
as it searches for food.
Right in the middle
of the abyssal plain
lie the largest geological
structures on our planet...
the mid-ocean ridges.
Rising almost two miles
off the sea floor,
the ridges extend
for over 28,000 miles,
the largest mountain chain on Earth.
When submersibles finally succeeded
in reaching the ridges in the 1970s,
they found an extraordinary world
with mile upon mile
of once molten rock
that had welled up from the deep
in the past and had now solidified.
They discovered towering chimneys,
pouring out water
as hot as molten lead.
At the surface, water becomes steam
at 100 degrees Centigrade,
but here, under the immense pressure
of the ocean,
it remains liquid at temperatures
as hot as 400 degrees Centigrade.
The submersible
has to move carefully.
Disaster is very close
when surrounded
by such enormous temperatures
and pressures.
And here,
where the very water is loaded
with hydrogen sulphides
poisonous to normal life processes,
they found living creatures.
Some of the chimneys
were encrusted with white tubes.
The tubes were inhabited
by a new species of polychaete worm
that was exposed to temperatures
as high as 80 degrees Centigrade.
No other animal on Earth was known
to tolerate such high temperatures,
so the scientists called
these creatures Pompeii worms.
But this was just the beginning.
Nearby, there were chimneys
covered by whole communities
of different organisms.
The bottom of the vent
was encrusted with large mussels.
There were swarms of white crabs,
and, most spectacular of all,
dominating the chimney were
hundreds of bright red tubeworms,
each two metres long
and four centimetres wide.
Until these creatures
were discovered,
all life on Earth was thought
to be dependent on the sun,
but here, in the complete darkness
of the deep,
they had discovered
a rich density of life
that derived no energy from the sun.
So what do they live on?
The answer was found
within the tubeworms themselves.
They were packed full
of specialised bacteria
that are able to derive energy
from the sulphides
that pour from the vents.
The worms' plumes were bright red
with haemoglobin
that carries sulphides and oxygen
down to the bacteria.
These bacterial colonies
are the primary source of energy
for all that lives here.
The mussels were packed with them.
just as green plants
are the basis of life
for animals living in the sun,
so these bacteria and other microbes
are at the foot of the food chain
on which over 500 species depend.
Crabs and shrimps feed off bacteria
and even try to steal pieces
of tubeworm plumes.
Since the vents were first visited
by biologists in 1979,
a new species has been described
every ten days.
At the top of the food chain, fish
that never stray far from the vents,
but they or their descendants
will move eventually,
for we now know that
individual vents are rarely active
for more than a few decades.
Such a density of life
living in such harsh conditions
in the middle of a vast
and otherwise barren abyssal plain
astounded the biologists
who first saw it.
it seemed to them that here was
evidence of how life on this planet,
which certainly started in the sea,
might have begun.
Deep sea submersibles
made an even more
extraordinary discovery in 1990.
0ver half a mile down,
at the bottom of the Gulf of Mexico,
they came across what appeared
to be an underwater lake,
over 20 metres long,
with its own sandy shore.
Around its edge,
there even seemed to be a tide line,
but this couldn't be, of course,
this was underwater.
in fact, the lapping edge
was created
by a thick soup of salty brine
far heavier than
the surrounding sea water,
and the sand was made up
of hundreds of thousands of mussels.
0nce again, in the midst
of a totally barren sea bed,
an extraordinarily
rich oasis of life
totally independent
of the sun's energy.
The source of energy this time
was not sulphides
but methane bubbling
out of the sea bed, and once again,
the mussels carried special bacteria
capable of fixing
the methane's energy.
just like the hot vents,
a complete ecosystem had developed
based on the bacteria.
There was an enormous variety
of completely new species - shrimps,
weird squat lobsters,
and bright red
polychaete worms.
These oases were called cold seeps
and were surprisingly similar
to the hot vents.
The geological processes
in the sea floor that produce methane
also tend to result in the release
of hydrogen sulphides.
it was hardly surprising, then,
when, not far from the brine pool,
they found tubeworms...
extensive fields of tubeworms
that stretch for hundreds of metres.
This new species also uses bacteria
to fix energy from sulphides,
but it extracts them directly
from the ground.
Their beautiful gills
are only used to supply oxygen
to the bacteria.
Amazingly, these tubeworms
are over 200 years old.
While hot vent tubeworms
may be the fastest-growing
invertebrates in the sea,
these appear to be far slower -
all the more reason to protect
your gills from biting amphipods.
The energy sources exploited
by the hot vent animals
may suddenly fail,
but here, life can enjoy
a more stable geological future.
To discover within ten years
two completely new ecosystems,
both totally independent
of the sun's energy,
has been quite extraordinary.
So far, we have explored just one
per cent of the deep ocean floor.
Who knows what is still out there
to be discovered?