This programme contains
some violent scenes and
strong language from the start.
Arthur.
John.
Michael.
The Chief Constable of Birmingham
has issued a warrant
for your arrest.
I've made a deal with people
even more powerful than our enemies.
Trust me, brother.
Father.
What is it - Sunday?
There's been a mistake.
There's an appeal process underway
that doesn't begin until January.
I want to see my lawyer, Mr Patrick.
Stop! This shouldn't be happening!
Get your hands off me!
Argh! Get your hands off me,
you bastards!
I'm John Shelby!
When I come back...when
I come back, got to be clear.
Want to go outside.
Michael! Michael!
Arthur! Michael! Arthur!
John! Where's Tommy?!
Arthur!
Arthur! JOHN!
No!
Arthur, you have to call the King!
About what? About this!
This is the case of a family
of Birmingham gangsters
on trial for murder and sedition.
Why would the King intervene?
The leader of the gang,
Thomas Shelby.
He claims his family was caught up
in a wider conspiracy.
He names Winston Churchill.
You woke me up for this?
And he also sent us this.
How the fuck did
a Birmingham racketeer
get his hands on a personal letter
written by King George?
During a robbery at Hampton Court,
Shelby discovered
a box of correspondence.
Among the papers he stole was
that letter from the King himself,
which proves
His Majesty was involved.
Oh, utter fuck.
If his family walks free, then he
will burn the papers in my presence.
When are they due to hang? Today.
This morning,
in Winson Green Prison.
Why the hell didn't you
bring it up before?!
The plan was for
the Lord Chamberlain
to intervene at the appeal
but late last night
some local judge brought
the executions forward.
Oh, my giddy aunt!
Put me through to His Majesty.
Well, wake him up!
In the bleak midwinter.
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done
on earth as it is...
Oh, Lord Jesus,
with this rope,
pull me up to heaven.
I see your face shining down on me!
Wait!
Also, sir, in return for
burning the King's letters,
Thomas Shelby has asked
for something else.
An inclusion in this year's
New Year's honours list.
Thomas Shelby has asked for
the King to award him an OBE, sir.
God bless. Merry Christmas!
Not going home for Christmas,
Mr Shelby?
Tomorrow.
So...Maria, or Clara, or Elizabeth?
It's Christmas.
Someone new, Billy.
I've wrapped all Charlie's presents
and left them in the room.
What did I get him?
Toy horses, toy cars, toy guns.
You're due at the Singer factory
at 8:00 tomorrow, not 8:30.
There's an union problem.
8:00. Yep.
Then the driver will take you home.
I'll drive myself.
Good night, Lizzie.
Have a good Christmas.
I'll have a vodka tonic. Yes, ma'am.
Tommy, I've had Christmas cards
from John, Arthur,
Ada, Michael and Polly.
And an invitation.
New Year's.
A party at John's house.
A party at John's big house.
Good for him.
Ada's coming back
from Boston for it.
I know.
It was me who gave her the time off.
Why don't you come?
Just turn up. Bring Charlie.
Bring a lump of coal. First footing.
A dark-haired man crosses
the threshold to bring good luck
for the new year. Hm?
The babies will make everybody OK.
Babies stop everything.
You can't pull a razor with
a baby there. Not even Esme.
Just come. See what happens.
Tommy, you've never even
seen Arthur's kid.
Nor John and Esme's.
Your drink, madam. Thank you.
Billy?
Who did you get for me?
Theresa. I said someone new.
Understood.
Do it for Charlie!
Charlie should know his cousins.
I got Charlie a real horse, Lizzie.
Not a toy. A thoroughbred.
And on Christmas Day,
it'll be just you and Charlie.
And the horse.
You can't live like this
another year.
Sex, freedom, whisky sours.
Which one should I give up first,
Lizzie, eh?
I've got you something.
Merry Christmas.
I told you, you didn't need to come
on Christmas Eve.
I could have dealt with it.
Yeah? Like you dealt with it
at the Pressings factory(!)
Well, this is the same problem.
Same fucking union convenor.
Area convenor for the Boilermakers'
Union has got involved in something
that could have otherwise been fixed
with a drink and a bribe.
The wire-cutting shop? Yeah.
Now, all the wire-cutters
here are women.
That's why the union convenor
thinks they're being underpaid.
Well, tell him there are no men
in the cutting shops,
so there can be no comparatives.
It's a woman. What is?
The union convenor
causing all the trouble.
Fuck! Her name's Jessie Eden.
You heard of her? Yeah.
Do you want me in the meeting?
No.
Michael?
Look...sometimes I have
a sniff of snow, so what?
How's your mother?
I drove past her house.
The drainpipe was hanging off.
Look, the cocaine keeps me awake.
Very long hours these days,
and when I do sleep,
I dream about what happened.
I wasn't asking
about you, Michael, was I?
I was asking about your mother.
Since she was pardoned,
she's been on these fucking tablets
the doctor gave her
when she was in the prison.
She says that when she was
inside the noose...she saw spirits.
She's running seances,
but people just come into
the house to steal things.
Tommy, it's bad.
All right, all right.
Hm! Now, listen to me, Michael...
..the spirits she sees are real.
Believe they're real.
Believe it with her.
Then eventually...
you can take the remembered noose
from around her neck...
..like a horse that's
been choked off.
Keep her off whisky,
throw away the tablets...
..and stop giving her fucking snow.
Fuck, Tommy, that sounded like
family advice.
Are you coming back?
Nothing to come back to.
Truth is, they're all fucked.
The lot of them. Yeah.
Find out about that woman,
Jessie Eden.
Don't let your mother keep cash
in the house. And, oi!
No cocaine
in my registered premises.
Did you see they all came?
Yeah, I saw you at the back.
It's funny they don't notice.
Oh, my sweet!
Oh, my heart!
Crushed to death in the canal.
But back home again,
and so beautiful!
Oh!
Inside the loop.
Inside the merry loop.
For fuck's sake!
Fucking birds!
Ada.
Come on.
I thought we'd lost you to
the great white way of Broadway.
No. Well, this beats
Watery Lane, John.
Does it?
Take a seat, I'll grab the kids.
Oh, it's all right,
I'm not stopping.
I just want to drop those presents
off for tomorrow.
I don't want words on Christmas Eve.
It's my house. You're welcome.
It's OK, I'm staying with Polly.
Yeah. She's in a bad way.
Mm. I'll bring her to her senses.
Michael's already tried that.
I'll get through to her.
You still going to come to
the party on New Year's Eve?
Yeah. Who else is coming?
Arthur, Linda...
Hello, Esme.
Who paid for your car and driver,
Ada?
Shelby Company Limited.
Nice car. He treats you well.
His last little pet.
Look, this visit is meant to be
about making things all right.
John had a rope around his neck.
He shit himself.
All right, Esme, that'll do, yeah?
Go in the kitchen.
Take a curse back to the money.
Anyway, there's your presents.
How's Arthur?
For Christmas,
get him a sewing kit...
..so he can sew
his fucking balls back on.
Oh!
Maypole 245.
Hello, Esme.
There you go, look. That's a couple
of eggs. Two eggs. There we go.
Arthur?
Be careful with Billy in there,
there's a cock.
Yeah, I will.
And don't smoke that near him.
All right. Get out of it!
Esme called to say
Ada's on her way over.
Did you hear that, Billy boy?
Your Auntie Ada's coming
all the way from America.
Bye, chickens!
Oh! We dropped an egg, look!
We dropped an egg, Billy boy.
Red Right Hand
by FIDLAR
Give him the hell he gives us,
Miss Eden.
Excuse me! This is the gents...
You don't have a women's lavatory
on the second floor
because no women get this far up.
If you don't have a women's
lavatory, I can't go to it, can I?
You say there is a disparity in pay
based on sex.
The male wire-cutters
in the Rover factory
a mile and a half down the road
are paid ten shillings a week more
than the female wire-cutters here.
Different factories,
different rates.
But both factories
are owned by you, Mr Shelby.
Not in your own name, of course.
In the name of Arrow House Holdings.
You own the Lanchester
car and van factory
in the name
of Tilton Company Limited,
the Billings machine tools factories
at Hay Mills and Greet
in the name of
Stetchford Engineering,
the Bilston Forgings and Pressings
factory in the name of Canalside,
and the canal warehousing
in Gas Street,
Saltely and Cadbury in the name
of Shelby Company Limited.
Also, 255 streets
of back-to-back houses.
Very good.
So this isn't about women and men.
It's about me, eh?
Tommy Shelby, OBE.
No, it's not about you.
It's about disparities.
It's about ten shillings a week
for working mothers
so they can buy shoes for their
kids. Never had shoes myself.
So, now you deny others?
And, barefoot, I grew up mean.
Oh, I know.
Oh, yeah, you know everything.
Your turn of phrase...
Is unacceptable?
You grew up mean, you say? A threat
in there, I think, somewhere.
No threats. The whole of
Birmingham knows you, Mr Shelby.
Sweetheart...whatever you've heard,
I don't need to make threats.
My comrade brothers and sisters...
Huh! Your brothers and sisters!
All right, listen,
I will conduct myself
as a businessman...
Who says "sweetheart"!
You say there is
a ten-shilling disparity
between male and female cutters
in two of my factories?
Very well.
I will increase the pay of
the female cutters
in this factory by five shillings.
And I will cut the pay
of the male cutters in the Rover
by five shillings...
..thereby achieving
your sacred fucking parity.
And I will tell the men
with families to feed
whose idea it was to cut their pay.
You do that, I will bring
all my members out on strike.
Oh, yeah? The week after Christmas?
You think so?
You know, everything
you've said here today,
and the fact that we're having
this meeting today
tells me that you are
a woman without a family.
And everything I hear about you
tells me you are a man
without a family, as well.
My comrade brothers and sisters
are not afraid of you, Mr Shelby.
I will call an extraordinary meeting
of my executive committee
as soon as Boxing Day.
You will hear the whistles blow
all across Birmingham.
I've heard lots of whistles blow,
sweetheart!
The post has arrived, Mr Shelby.
I'm sorry to keep asking,
but Chef needs to know
how many for dinner tomorrow.
He's new. He's foreign.
He gets very upset.
Right. Well, you tell Chef
there'll be 27 guests
for Christmas dinner tomorrow.
27? Family?
Yep. I thought Charlie
could do with some company,
so I asked Johnny Dogs if he knew
anyone who liked to eat goose...
..and he said he knew 26.
Tell Chef I want ten geese,
a buck cut into steaks,
some trout from the river.
Fetch whisky, brandy and wine
from the cellar. Best we have.
There will be children?
Lots of children.
With Johnny's tribe, new ones
might be born on the floor.
So have mops and buckets ready, eh?
And I want you at the table,
Frances, so make it 28.
I will be busy.
You've put up with me
this past year,
looked after Charlie
when I've been on business.
Tomorrow, you will eat at my table.
Things will get better, I think,
next year.
It gets much warmer
than here in the summer.
Much colder in the winter.
I knew it. Mm.
But parts of it are
just like Birmingham.
Yeah. Shit and smoke
are the same everywhere.
Hm. What about you, Linda?
Are you working?
I've been seeking work as a teacher.
A teacher.
But, you know, it's quite difficult.
The Shelby name,
it's always in the papers.
And, er...what do you
get up to all day, Arthur?
As you know,
Arthur's previous endeavours
have left us with
no need for a salary.
Arthur occupies his time in
the garden, doing voluntary work.
He drives old people and cripples.
Oh. Yeah, well,
it's something to do.
I want to open a garage.
Some day. Fixing cars, you know?
Sometimes cars attract
ambitious men.
Yeah, well...I like fixing cars.
I'll go. I got it.
Maypole 245.
Arthur, have you checked your post?
I just got served a black hand.
I just got delivered a black fucking
hand to the house.
From Luca Changretta.
Jesus!
Jesus Christ!
Wait a minute, John,
which one was Luca?
The old man's oldest son.
He was going to get done for
killing a bank clerk in a robbery,
so his old man sent him
back to New York.
You know what the black hand means
among the wops, Arthur?
It's Mafia shit.
The Sicilian fucking Mafia!
Check your post, Arthur.
Arthur, I was just leaving.
No, you're not.
I need...I need to talk to you.
Arthur?
It's all right, Linda. Stay here.
Ada, please.
Linda? You stay here.
Did you say Mafia?
Esme, I need to make a call. No!
I need to make a fucking call! Give
it here! What the fuck is this?!
Give it here! Not until you tell me
what the fuck it is!
Give it here! What is it?!
It's from Luca Changretta,
all right? We killed his dad.
I remember.
It was Tommy who killed him!
It was fucking Arthur
pulled the trigger!
All right, it was mercy,
but it was Arthur!
Anyway,
it makes no fucking difference!
For the wops, it's family.
The black hand came here.
Everybody will have got one.
They're coming for us all!
We made an agreement.
We made a solemn promise.
We're the family now.
Here, look at that.
That's from Changretta's son, Luca.
How the fuck he
knows where I live. Eh?
And why's he waited a year?
I'm going to see Tommy next.
I'll talk to him.
I've been served a black hand
and she won't even let me
keep a fucking
spud gun in the house.
Go to a hotel.
It's Christmas Eve, Ada.
I've got a gun in the glove
compartment. You take that for now.
I'll talk to Tommy
and have him call.
Just make sure you get to the
phone first. Yeah. Now hug me,
like you came out here
because you were emotional.
I am emotional. I just don't know
what fucking emotion it is.
It'll be OK. I'll talk to Tommy.
You talk to him.
You and me both, brother.
Ada!
You wait there,
you won't leave empty handed.
Here you go, look, some eggs,
you give them to Polly, all right?
And you, keep your eyes on the road.
Take care.
Who was on the phone, Arthur?
John. Wishing me Merry Christmas.
Come inside. It's getting late.
Thanks.
Take off the hat.
Are you with those other Italians?
We're Americans.
It says it right there on the paper.
USA.
And what's the purpose
of your visit?
Pleasure.
Mum? It's me.
You left the door open.
To change the air.
I told you I was busy today.
What do you want?
Why haven't you opened your post?
I tidied up.
Ada's coming today.
She's late.
Tommy asked about you today.
I hope Ada's car hasn't broken down.
Is Shelby Company Limited
still using Bentleys?
Yeah.
Bentleys are no good in the cold.
You should tell him.
I will.
Any other messages for Tommy?
Yeah. Fuck off.
He saw that your drain pipe
was broken. He was worried.
Is that it? Is that all
he asked about? Drainpipes?
No. He said that I'm to accept
that you have a gift.
That you've always had a gift.
What gift?
Second sight.
Spirits. All that gypsy stuff,
he said that I'm to believe you.
You think I don't
hear his voice in yours.
You don't think
I recognise his strategies.
I'm still a match for him.
Yes.
You are. And you still can be.
Me and Lizzie decided that
this New Year
we're all to turn the page.
You can't spend another
year like this, Mum. "Mum."
Mum.
That word is like a bullet to me.
I see your sister in
that chair sometimes...
Look, me and Lizzie
have decided.
It's time.
I bought these.
One for you and Ada
and one for you and me.
So Tommy said,
"Keep her off the whisky."
I'll drink Champagne
the day my son leaves
the employment
of Shelby Company Limited.
You tell him that next time
he mentions fucking drainpipes.
Right. Now, this is your job,
Charlie. We give those to Santa
and Rudolph.
Good boy. Put this out for Santa,
for his whisky.
Now, night-night. Merry Christmas.
I will see you tomorrow. Sleep well.
Come on, Charlie.
Mr Shelby, it's your sister.
I know. Send her in.
I got a card, Ada.
I'm guessing Arthur
and John have had one as well.
Hello, Tommy. "Hello, Ada, welcome
home." Thanks, it's nice to be back.
I've spoken to Moss.
Moss said Changretta is a soldier
for the Spinetti family,
which means he will have men
with him, professional men.
They usually operate in
units of around ten.
Moss is checking Cunard records to
see if they're already in England.
This one's for you.
What is it? A time machine?
My God. Tommy Shelby.
Is that regret?
I'll open it tomorrow.
So, boss, in the light of
the changed circumstances,
what are your orders?
Changretta knows where we all live.
If we stay out
in the open, isolated,
he'll pick us off one by one.
We need to be together in a place
even they won't dare to come.
You mean back home?
Within a four-mile radius
of the Garrison,
every man is a guard
and a soldier for us.
I'm calling a family meeting.
Charlie Strong's yard, Boxing Day.
Finn's already there.
You tell Polly and Michael.
I'll deal with John and Arthur.
And Esme and Linda?
Anyone who wants to live
to see another Christmas
needs to come to where it's safe.
These bastards
will kill kids as well.
When this business is finished,
we can...go our separate ways.
Go and see Polly and explain.
She'll have had a card as well.
Do you think I'm on the list?
We're all on the list, Ada.
I gave my gun to Arthur.
Welcome home.
Holy shit, it's Father Christmas.
Yeah, and if you're good...
you get what you deserve.
Fucking come here, you!
Fuck.
Yeah, put me through to Maypole 245.
Hello. Arthur, it's Tommy.
Be quick, they're asleep.
Family meeting,
Charlie's yard, Boxing Day, midday.
I can't raise John but
I'll send Michael to get him.
If you have to pull a gun on Linda,
do it. Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas, Tom.
What did you do with them?
My tablets were in
the bathroom cabinet.
What did you do with them?
I threw them in the lavatory.
Tommy's orders?
No. My own decision.
How am I going to get through
Christmas without them?
They close everything.
How am I going to get through
Christmas without them?
I'll help you.
They don't open anything.
Fucking no apothecary, nothing.
You can move in with me
and I'll help you.
How can I get through
fucking Christmas? Without...
Without anything! How?
You can move in with me
and I'll help you.
Fuck off! Fuck off!
Fuck off, Thomas Shelby!
Fuck off! It's all right it's me.
Mum, this as got to stop!
I don't want you,
I don't want you, Thomas Shelby.
My husband is back and he loves me.
Tommy said to believe in
spirits with you, but I can't.
Hello, Polly. Hello, Michael.
Merry Christmas.
The door was wide open.
Fuck.
I spent the whole day tidying up.
I wanted it to be nice.
I wanted it to look nice!
Why, Pol? It's only me.
It's OK. It's OK.
We can sit, sit and talk
and put things back together.
It's OK.
I'll leave you two to it.
No, you stay.
Now, listen, something's happened.
Things have changed.
Today everyone in the family
received one of these.
What does it mean?
Tommy's called a family meeting.
He wants you both to come.
Come.
I'm really sorry to
bother you again, sir,
but Chef insists on knowing
what time the guests will arrive.
Francis, for the last time,
it's Johnny Dogs. They're gypsies.
They're camped down by the river.
When they're ready
they'll walk up. All right?
He says it's about preparation, sir.
What is?
He's asked specifically.
Will they arrive before
the King's speech or after?
You said he was new, this chef.
When did join us?
October.
And he's foreign?
He's Italian, sir.
Oh. He's the best chef we've
ever had in the house.
No shouting or swearing
or blaspheming.
Do we have his references?
Yes.
The only problem
has been his assistant.
What assistant?
He brought an assistant with him.
He calls him his sous-chef.
Are they still working, Frances?
They'll be there till midnight, sir.
Right, thank you. Good night.
You can go to bed.
Merry Christmas, sir.
And I thought about your offer.
I'd be happy to sit at your table.
Right, thank you.
What's your name?
Max, Mr Shelby.
Max.
It's all right. Don't get up.
Oh. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry, yes.
You're new. I'm Mr Shelby.
Hello, sir.
I haven't taken time to
introduce myself.
Antonio.
What have you done
that's so wrong, eh?
Excuse me?
A sous-chef peeling potatoes.
It's an emergency. Late notice.
Oh. Late notice.
Right, right, carry on.
Antonio...
..here, 10£.
For the late notice.
You wanted to know if
my guests would arrive
before or after the King's speech?
Eh? Yes.
It'll be after.
How are you?
Oh, just...worried about tomorrow.
Yeah? I'm worried about Antonio.
You've been here two months
and we've not met before.
It's my fault. I've been busy.
Thomas Shelby.
My hand has blood.
Oh, mine too.
Hey, er, how much do
you pay Antonio?
I forget.
Must be a lot.
I just gave him ?10.
Didn't mean a fucking thing to him.
Maybe it isn't you that pays him.
I've been reading up on you.
Bertorelli. Claridge's.
You used to work in a place
called San Marco's,
on...on Fleet Street.
I used to know the man
that owned San Marco's.
A man called Darby Sabini.
I never met him. No.
Maybe your...assistant, Antonio,
maybe he's met him.
Here's how it is.
Antonio was sent from New York.
I don't know. Please...
Darby Sabini facilitated.
He passed him on to you and told
you to bring him into my house.
They threatened to kill you
if you didn't do it.
You want me to dress you like
you dressed that fucking stag?
Please!
You know about me, right? Mm-hm.
You know what I do? Mm-hm.
You wanted to know when
my guests would arrive
because Antonio needed me alone.
He's an assassin.
The plan is to kill me tomorrow.
I don't know.
They just said bring him here.
Well, bring him here.
Antonio!
You are a black hand!
How many came from New York?
How many fucking came from New York?
Vaffanculo!
What did he... What did he say?
Is that a curse or a number?
What did he fucking say?
He said, "Fuck you." Yeah?
The black hand means
kill or be killed.
You go back to London,
you tell Darby Sabini he picked
the wrong side in this war.
Once we've dealt with the Americans,
we'll come for him.
Go on, go.
Go.
Oi! You tell anyone else,
I'll come and find you.
Harrow 335.
The Hare and Hounds pub.
Robert. Yes, it's Mr Shelby.
Merry Christmas to you too.
Robert, is there a gypsy in
the public bar playing
the fiddle for shillings?
Yes.
Can you, er, can you tell him
I need to speak to him?
Thank you.
Oh, fuck, Tom.
I thought these sporting
days were over.
Yeah, so did I.
But they keep coming back at us.
There's a black stallion
in the stables.
He's invisible at night, use him.
Take the body across the river
to the rough ground.
Burn him? No. This one's a message.
Will there still be
geese for dinner?
Only if you can steal them
on the way. On the way where?
We're going back, Johnny.
Back to Small Heath.
Back where you belong.
Merry Christmas.
You can keep the stallion.
Christ the fucking night.
Michael, they're coming today.
Michael, shut up and listen.
You've got to get everyone out.
Get Polly and Ada to Charlie's yard.
I've told Arthur
but I can't reach John.
When you've dropped Polly and Ada,
go out to John's place
and get him out. All right?
Is it Christmas?
Not just yet. Let's go, eh? Mummy!
Move!
Hello?
Oh, fuck. It's you. Got nothing
better to do on Christmas morning?
Tommy wants everybody at
Charlie's yard now. Come on.
Get in. Get in. What's going to
happen? It's fucking Christmas.
Look, John, we don't
have time for this.
Come into the house. Just come
to the meeting. Have some food.
Tell Tommy Shelby
we can look after ourselves.
Tommy says they could
come for us today.
Tommy says, Tommy says.
Are you his fucking parrot?
Look it's the Mafia, all right.
This is the New York Mafia
we're talking about.
And we're
the Peaky fucking Blinders.
No, we're not, John.
We're not the Peaky fucking Blinders
unless we're together.
You were together on the gallows,
with one man missing.
John? John, come to the meeting,
all right? Think about the kids.
Come to the meeting and
if you want to leave then fine.
No. It's Christmas Day.
We're the family now.
We're staying at home.
In the fucking house! Esme...
John!
.::Sub#One::.