If the Italians win, they're not leaving.
They're coming and they're here to stay.
The intelligence services in London
sent seven officers to Birmingham.
At the top of their list is Ada Thorne.
Alfie Solomons runs the fighter.
He says it's money for nothing.
That there is the Southern
Counties welterweight champion.
Name the day, Mr Shelby.
Stop drinking whisky, switch to stout,
then go and see a doctor about that baby.
Make sure Tommy keeps that Friday free.
Tell him I have an appointment for him.
You've agreed to give up Tommy...
..to save my life.
This programme contains some violent
scenes and very strong language
Shoot out his tyres.
But remember, I fire the final shot!
Stay inside, love!
Come on!
Go. Go. Go!
It's all right, love. It's all
right. Come inside. Come inside.
Stay inside, don't come out.
Get away from the window.
Right, stay inside and stay down.
Everyone, stay indoors, stay down!
By order of the Peaky Blinders!
Come on!
Come here.
Which way? Which way did he go?
You sure?
Oi!
Luca.
_
No!
Hey, I know you own the cops in
this dirty
fucking town, but you'll be dead
before they get here!
Come on. Me and you, Tommy, come on!
_
Enough! I said enough!
I said enough! Now get out of it!
Go on. Enough!
What the fuck are you doing here?
Saving your life.
Or his. I'm a police officer, Tommy,
I'm a fucking police officer, right?
Doing my duty.
Stopping all this!
There's three bodies need cleaning up.
No. Enough.
Tell the people who live in these houses
that they are free to go about their
lawful business.
Tell them that the rule of law has
been restored.
Haven't you heard, Tommy? Hey?
Soldiers are coming.
Do you know, I remember the very
first time
you head butted a policeman.
And after you got your OBE from the King,
I didn't think there'd be a next time.
What do you think you're going to
tell Arthur?
I'll tell him the truth.
They're here.
So. What the fuck happened today, Tom?
We all heard, shooting
in Artillery Square.
Yeah, there was.
Today I killed three men.
Now our enemies are down to eight.
I suppose they, er, I suppose they
took you by surprise, did they?
No. I knew they were coming.
Just after Christmas, I received a
letter from Luca Changretta...
..offering to spare my son if I gave
up Tommy...
..and I gave Tommy up.
Because that was the plan that
Polly and I agreed on.
I knew that Luca would want to pull
the trigger himself,
so I used the set-up as bait to
bring him here.
You're a fucking idiot, Tom!
Look, I didn't get Luca but I got
three, all right? That's it.
That's what happened.
Come here, you. Aye, but he's right, ah.
I mean, I thought you'd gone soft.
So you got three?
Yeah, I got three.
Well, I'll drink to you, Tom, you
mad bastard.
Pretty soon you'll... You're going
to get the shakes
when your blood cools down. Let's go
and get a drink.
Dad? You got three what?
I got three shillings for a two
shilling horse, my boy.
You come with us, eh?
You want a drink, Lizzie? I've had a
hard day.
I don't drink whisky or gin any
more, Tom.
Why not?
Because they say it harms the baby.
Yes, it can only be yours.
That day by the canal
when you were fucking somebody else
in your head.
Except it wasn't her who got pregnant.
Have a seat, Lizzie.
All right, I know a woman, Lizzie...
You know lots of women, Tommy.
If you don't know this already, you
don't know me -
I'm keeping it.
Who's going to run my fucking office?
You'll find somebody.
Well, you'd better put a fucking
advert in the paper, then.
I'm not laid up yet.
You'll not go to work with a child
of mine inside of you.
Fuck, now my hand shakes...
It's OK, Tom. We'll be OK.
All this death, Lizzie. Fuck,
let's have some life, eh?
I got three.
I know, Tom.
One of them point-blank.
A baby. A little you and me.
Point-blank, Lizzie.
And he looked up at me.
You'll get an allowance...
..every week, from the company.
Business is booming.
We'll, erm, buy a nice house, eh?
Come on, I'll drive you home.
I'm just looking.
Hm?
DOOR OPENS Fuck! Linda?
Arthur, you scared me to death.
Linda, oh...
Linda, I need you to save me... again.
You're drunk... again.
I'm drunk again.
I am drunk again.
I need you to save me.
Tell me what you said to me this morning.
Tell me. Tell me again.
Tell me, say it. Say it.
Tell me.
We will be back in our garden
before the time comes to plant
anything out.
Just one winter.
Come to bed, Arthur.
They're coming, boys.
No! No! No fucking way!
You've never eaten hedgehog, Michael?
I'm getting back in this car.
Michael, you're number two on Luca
Changretta's hit list.
Yeah, and I'll stay in a hotel.
You stay in a hotel, I'll know
where you are,
so will the people who take you there,
so will the people who work in the hotel,
and hotels don't move around.
They don't even know where they'll
be tomorrow.
They follow the Patrin and the crows.
And if anyone should come for you,
Michael,
the Palmers and the Boswells will
put up a fair fight.
Take your medicine.
- I'll take them.
- Your painkillers...
The healers up there will heal you
much quicker.
Fucking witches, the lot of them.
Show some respect, Mr Gray.
They have agreed to welcome you on
account of your blood.
Take your medicine, take the gun.
I won't be able to contact you, so
you phone me.
We'll make a plan.
Tommy says it won't be long. Then
we'll be free.
You might learn something.
Tell them your grandmother was a
Gypsy princess,
name of Birdie Boswell.
You're royalty up there, Michael.
Is that true, Mrs Gray?
What? Don't I look like royalty?
Now that you mention it, you do.
I've been cooped up in Small Heath
too long.
I can smell spring in the air.
Do you know a longer way back, Mr Gold?
I know ways back that would take forever.
Get in, Your Majesty.
I thought you were a busy woman.
Do you have time for this?
Is it a buck?
It is a buck.
Good. Bucks taste better.
In the smoke I'm 16 again.
You know, when the police were after
him, our dad used to take us out.
We'd be gone for days, living on
what he caught.
Oh, do you have a sharp knife?
I heard you have second sight.
I heard that you speak with the dead.
Yes.
Your wife is often around you.
She watches you.
Is she watching me now?
No.
Your family were healers?
Yeah, a long time ago.
Came back when I put my head in the
noose.
It's like putting your head through
a window and seeing the whole world.
Give me the rabbit...
..and the knife.
You know, Polly, I believe it's
you who's kept Tommy Shelby alive
all these years.
Oh, we've kept each other alive.
But I didn't just put my head
through that window...
..I climbed through it.
First I thought it was madness, but no.
When you've put your head out of
that window
you can do anything
you want,
cos there are no rules...
..cos there are no risks.
Now give me the knife.
Now, come here.
I can do whatever I want...
..whenever the mood takes me.
And you are a strong, handsome man...
..and this is a beautiful place in
the world...
..and it is this time...
But let me make one thing clear, Mr Gold,
I just gave Michael a little speech
about how no-one would know how to
find him...
..but you'd know how to get him.
If any harm comes to Michael, you
shall have me as your enemy.
And none of your knives can kill me.
Do you understand?
Oh, I understand.
Tute's a rinkeni moola.
_
Abri.
Mr Solomons?
Hm!
My little cousin was born blind,
but as a result I now donate a
considerable sum of money
to a charity which gives dogs with
eyes to blind Jews.
The chairman of the board recommends
that those of us
who were blessed with the gift of sight,
that we spend, you know,
at least half an hour of our day
with our eyes closed
so that we may, well, we may better
understand the, er...
..the darkness and also to increase
our donations and that.
What time is it?
- 29 minutes past eight.
- Right.
Well, then I have... I have another
minute to go, actually,
but you, er,
you can begin.
Go on.
I'm Luca Changretta.
Oh, yeah, I know who you are.
You are a bit of a failure, aren't you?
You come all the way over here to
this country
in order to kill Tommy Shelby,
but, I mean, well, he's not dead, is he?
So... No.
- No.
- He ain't.
How much time have I got left, mate?
Ten seconds, nine seconds,
eight seconds...
..five, four, three, two, one.
Right, hello. How can I help you?
I have a proposition for you.
Hmm, yeah, it's... I already know
what you want, yeah,
but I just want to hear you say it
out loud
so I can check how ridiculous it is.
OK.
We hear there's going to be a little
fight, you know,
a boxing match,
between your boy and Tommy Shelby's
boy, in Birmingham.
Yep.
And the whole Shelby family's
going to be there.
And you, Mr Solomons, you too will
be there.
That's it. I'll tell you what, right?
Here's a gift, it's free - a
souvenir of your visit here.
Goodbye, trot on. Down there is
Bonnie Street.
You know, they say you are a smart guy.
You already know what we want before
we say it.
That's funny cos now
I believe I know what you want even
before you say it.
So, you going to taste it?
_
Damn fucking straight, mate,
otherwise you wouldn't still be
thieving my oxygen, would you?
Because I have 200 barrels a month, yeah,
cleared by your people, distributed
through your teamsters.
Thing is that people want gin these days.
Well, the exit is still out there,
right, on Bonnie Street. Yeah?
You're fucking crazy, you know
that? 200 barrels, ah?
What do you think, cousin?
But also I want some cash...
..bung work. That's why I've broken
it down here -
a list of costs pertaining to the
assassination
of a dear friend, all right?
Now, a normal dispatch, well, it's,
you know, £500 cost.
But you're going to have to add
another 100 to that
because Tommy Shelby, like me, is
from an oppressed people,
and I need you to put another tonne
on top of that
because his brother is a fucking
animal and he will come after me.
And then you will need to put
another 100 on top of that
because, well, you are a fucking
wop, mate, hmmm?
And you.
And then we've got to deal with the
ugly business,
which I've been incredibly clear of
before.
I will need another £500,
because, like I stated, Tommy Shelby
is a very, very good friend of mine.
Total...
..is down there in black and white,
all right? Crack on.
It's OK.
Mr Solomons, I'm going to be very
fucking clear with you.
I don't need you to kill anybody.
I have people that I trust.
So, you're going to take my boys
and you're going to bring them to
the ring as seconds.
Well, in order to qualify as my seconds
they would first have to qualify as
being Jewish.
Yeah?
And in order to do that, they would
have to replace their natural
Italian fucking arrogance with a
Jewish air of absolute certainty.
See, my good friend Thomas Shelby,
he will know the difference.
These days, back in the old
country, a lot of the, er, you know,
the Jewish people, they, er...
..they are having to pass themselves
off as Italian.
Right, well, you will have to add
another tonne on to your bill
for being a cunt, mate.
All right?
You will bring my men to Birmingham?
You will circumcise them.
You will have to circumcise them
because the Peakys will check.
Yeah?
OK. Any other request, eh?
200 fucking barrels, we have a deal.
Nah.
- What going on?
- Oh, well.
I said we have a deal.
Aye, you've just made a deal
without negotiation, didn't you?
Yeah, Tommy Shelby was right about
you, weren't he?
_
Ada Shelby?
No.
She was armed when we picked her
up, sir, so we strip searched her.
- That'll be all.
- Yes, sir.
I apologise, Miss Shelby,
the Territorials can be over zealous.
Your men watched.
Then they will be reprimanded.
They won't see Saturday.
A naked woman, alone, making threats
against the entire British Army -
a significant indicator of character.
I'll turn my back while you dress
and perhaps we can talk.
I have a dossier on each member of
your family.
I know your family's extraordinary
history.
Ah, fuck you.
I also have a totally blank page
on which together
we can write your family's immediate
future.
You rehearsed your speech -
significant indicator of a lack of
confidence.
What rank are you?
Colonel. May I turn...?
Not unless you want to get blinded.
I'm sorry. This has got off to a
bad start.
What is "this"?
Three days ago you were seen at a meeting
for the Stetchford Communist Party.
You were then seen talking to a
woman called Jessie Eden.
Turn around.
I'm leaving.
And you can burn this. It's history.
Ada Shelby.
A person of interest and under the
surveillance of Special Branch
since you joined the Birmingham
Communist Party in June 1919.
I'm no longer a member of the
Communist Party.
I know. Irrelevant.
Most of the more active subversives
shed their official allegiances to
avoid detection.
Look, OK, let me explain it to you.
I'm no longer a member of the
Communist Party
because I'm no longer a believer in
the cause of socialism.
Now, open that door!
So, in the past, you were blinded
by love.
No, blinded by faith. I believed
people deserve justice. They don't.
So, you've arrested me because I had
a drink with Jessie Eden.
Whisky with ice for you, and a
beer for her.
I met Jessie Eden to settle an
industrial dispute.
Head of acquisitions. So, you've
swapped sides.
If you know what I drink, you know
what I do for a living.
Mrs Shelby, you must understand
that these are extraordinary times.
A general strike is certain, an
attempted revolution perhaps,
soldiers on the streets very soon.
They're already drilling.
And here stands you, a woman with
her foot in both camps.
Potentially very useful.
Useful to who?
Maybe you should ask your brother,
Thomas.
Put some fucking effort into it, son.
The fight is in two days.
Get used to the reach.
Get used to the long arm on him.
Just get under it!
That's it, under his body.
Talk to me about Colonel Ben Younger.
What about him?
He's just made me a proposition.
You're in my chair.
He said you knew about it.
And, remember, I know when you're lying.
Ben Younger was an officer
with the Warwickshire Yeomanry in
Flanders.
The only cavalryman who could ride a
fucking horse.
I was strip searched.
Two soldiers watched.
I'm sorry, Ada.
The arrest was so the neighbours
would see and word would go round.
Younger is all right.
Younger came to me for help.
He's been given Birmingham.
"Given Birmingham" by who?
By Churchill, by the fucking King,
by people who want to stop a revolution.
No-one's laughing any more, Ada.
The Home Office is making provisions.
This is part of those provisions.
And how is Tommy Shelby OBE going
to stop a revolution?
Jessie Eden has accepted my
invitation to dinner.
Ah. Of course!
I'm sorry, Tommy Shelby is going to
stop the revolution with his cock!
It's not her the military are
interested in,
it's the people around her.
They're people like you used to be,
like Freddie used to be.
People who want an armed revolution.
If I get Jessie Eden's trust...
..she gives me the nose of the
instigators...
..I give 'em up to the Crown forces.
Tommy, Tommy, sweetheart...
..why would a man whose medals rust
at the bottom of the Saltley canal
want to help the British military?
Because I've been offered three
five-year contracts
to supply military vehicles
to the British forces
in India, Ceylon, Singapore and Burma,
total value - £2 million.
And there'll be no strikes in your
factory
because Jessie Eden will be in your bed.
Tommy, this can only happen if
you're still alive.
I'm planning on staying alive.
If I'm dead, you can all go back to
being what you were.
The British Army came to me, Ada.
I said, "Why not?"
They'll put that on your grave, Tom.
'Tommy Shelby - "Why not?"'
Are you going to help me or not?
Other way round.
Will they want music, Charlie?
We have that gramophone
we found abandoned inside that
gentleman's car.
No, they don't. Tommy said they're
here to talk.
Charlie, Curly, this is Jessie Eden.
Jessie, this is my Uncle Charlie and
my... whatever Curly is.
This is actually lovely.
We were just wondering if you'd
like some music.
- No, we weren't.
- Actually, Jessie likes music.
Don't go to any trouble.
No, Curly, go to some trouble.
Go on, then.
Right...
Don't I get a choice?
I want an opinion. Try it.
I don't really drink gin.
Then you're perfect.
My gin is for women that don't
really drink gin.
Your gin?
Let's drink to something. You choose.
To the revolution.
Why not?
- To the revolution.
- The revolution.
Right, well, since I invited you for
dinner, I thought I'd cook.
These two beauties were shot this morning
by a poacher friend of mine on Lord
Packwood's estate.
I thought you'd like that.
And these here, these were stolen
from under his trees.
Mr Shelby...
..I came to talk business.
Yes, so did I.
Wage cuts withdrawn,
parity between men and women guaranteed.
You can instruct your members to
return to work tomorrow.
And all I have to do in return
is tell you everything I know about
socialism.
That's what your sister said.
You don't like your gin?
It's OK.
It's OK?
What do you want to know about the cause?
I'm approaching the current
political crisis
as I would approach a horse race...
..assessing the runners and the riders.
Now, the favourite is, of course,
the King's horse.
But the King's horse was also the
favourite in 1913,
when Emily Davison threw herself in
front of it.
You know the names of
suffragettes. I'm impressed.
Everyone laughed at them at first,
but now look -
women with serious faces everywhere.
When I study a horse race, I study form.
And then the other horse,
the one who wants to beat
the King's horse...
Let's call her Dangerous, shall we?
..she's no form.
That's what makes her so dangerous.
Russia. Isn't that form?
No, the Russians aren't like the
English. We're beer, they're petrol.
That's why I invited you here for dinner.
I'm guessing you know people...
..people that want to make this
fight real,
with guns and ammunition.
So, before I place a bet on who's
going to win,
I need to know how strong they are...
..how serious they are.
Your concern is that if the
unthinkable happened...
..you would find yourself on the
wrong side of the barricades.
Well, as you can see,
my natural side of the barricades is
the same as yours.
And, as you know,
I once believed.
But the war changed you.
Yeah.
The man I loved couldn't speak
when he got back.
Not one word.
I've said very few true words since.
The men who blew the whistles in
France are our enemy.
And you count yourself among those
who want a real fight?
I do.
Well, well.
Yes. Not just in my dreams, in the
day now.
And you're not alone.
I am not alone.
Well, well.
I have researched you.
We have researched you.
You have never been a friend of the
Government.
They have used you.
And I imagine you have found out already
that no amount of money allows you
to pass through the steel sheets
that separate class from class.
Yes.
Yes, that I have learnt.
Men like you would terrify them -
a man better than them at what they do.
Would I change the odds, do you think?
It's all wound up, Tom.
Er, you just put the needle on and
let it spin.
And there are some popular records.
Mostly romantic.
Thank you, Curly.
Food's nearly ready.
Let's eat before we dance, shall we?
So we're going to dance?
I think so.
I swear to God.
She gave me sixpence and she sends
me to the shop
for margarine, eggs and bread.
And I came back...
With a top hat and a coconut?
That was all our money we had for
the whole fucking week
and my mum beat me with a fucking
frying pan.
Why the hell did you buy a top hat
and a coconut?
Cos I thought she deserved it. I
thought we all did.
And I could never understand
why people like us
only had bread and fucking lard...
..and I wanted to be different.
That's what I wanted.
And you are.
Well...
When I showed you that photo of
Greta Jurossi, your face changed.
She wanted everything to be different -
the whole world.
As do I.
Shall we have some more music?
You were married but she was killed.
Bye-bye Blackbird reminds you of
your sweetheart, eh?
Yes.
Right, fast or slow?
Better be slow. I'd better just sit.
I'm drunk.
Come on.
Will you help us, Tommy?
Soon. Soon.
Arrange a meeting with the
appropriate people
and I'll be there.
Vinny, come on, boy. Get over
here, you lazy bastard!
Here, want some of that?
The, er, room is clean, Mr Shelby.
Right. Lock it all down.
All right, boys, lock it down.
No weapons! No admission if you've
any weapon.
Go on!
Arthur!
Can I open the book?
Right, open it up. You!
Gentlemen.
Now, you listen to me, you put all
your money on the gold, you hear me?
It's fucking fight night.
Come on, boys, and place your bets
with me, Honest Johnny Dogs.
The only show in town, by order of
our special constable brothers,
the Peaky fucking Blinders.
Bonnie boy. Here we go, boy. Bring
out that fucking tiger.
Go on.
Tiger's already out.
Fair enough.
Bonnie.
Mr Shelby will give you a 20% cut
if you put Goliath down in the
fourth round.
Been caged up too long, brother.
If the women are going to have fun,
so am I.