- PREVIOUSLY ON DEXTER...
[Harrison crying]
MY WIFE DIED
AND IT WAS MY FAULT.
- YOUR DEAD WIFE
CAN SUCK MY DICK.
- THAT'S THE FIRST
HUMAN THING
I'VE SEEN YOU DO
SINCE SHE DIED, DEXTER.
- [screams]
- I DON'T WANT
TO LIVE WITH YOU.
I WANT TO LIVE
WITH GRANDMA AND GRANDPA.
- FBI.
FUCKING BUNCH OF IDIOTS.
- WE KNOW YOU DIDN'T
KILL YOUR WIFE.
- WE'RE JUST LOOKING FOR
A REASON WHY ARTHUR MITCHELL
MIGHT HAVE TARGETED HER.
- WE ALL GOOD HERE?
- THE ONLY LEAD WE HAVE NOW
IS THIS KYLE BUTLER.
- IT LOOKS LIKE SANTA MUERTE,
THE CULT.
- WHO ARE YOU?
- OFFICER MANZON, CIRA.
- WE HAVE SEX ONE DAY
AND THEN--
- I'M SORRY,
I'M NOT THE KIND OF PERSON
WHO WOULD EVER HAVE SEX
WITH YOU.
OKAY, WE HAD SEX.
- WAS IT GOOD SEX?
- I'VE SAID ALL I'M GONNA SAY.
- YOU'RE WELCOME
TO STAY HERE
FOR AS LONG AS YOU WANT,
WHENEVER YOU WANT.
I HEARD THE FBI INTERVIEW
WENT WELL.
- THEY'RE LOOKING FOR SOMEONE
NAMED KYLE BUTLER.
HE'S A FRIEND
OF ARTHUR MITCHELL'S.
THEY'VE HAVING SKETCHES DONE.
- THE MITCHELL FAMILY ALL GAVE
VERY DIFFERENT VERSIONS.
- DO YOU MIND IF I KEEP
A COPY OF THESE?
- YOU MARRIED MARIA LAGUERTA?
SUCH A FINE PIECE OF ASS.
- YOU FUCK!
[overlapping grunting]
- BOYD FOWLER.
YOU'RE PROBABLY USED TO SEEING
DEAD THINGS THOUGH, HUH?
- CAN'T SAY I EVER GET
USED TO IT.
- YOU WANT THAT NICE HOUSE
ON THE BEACH.
both: TAKE IT!
- I CAN SEE HAVING AN
OLD GIRLFRIEND'S LOCK OF HAIR,
BUT IDENTIFIED
BY ONLY A NUMBER?
[quirky music]
* *
- I'M JUST TRYING
TO GET TO THE TRUTH.
HOWEVER LONG THAT TAKES
IS UP TO YOU.
- I'M TELLING YOU THE TRUTH.
I'M NOT LYING.
- FIRST, YOU SAID YOU
DIDN'T DO DRUGS
AND THEN YOU SAID YOU DID.
- I SAID I MIGHT HAVE
TRIED SOME
AT A TRIDELT PARTY ONCE.
- YOU MIGHT HAVE?
WHAT THE FUCK DOES
THAT EVEN MEAN?
YOU DID OR YOU DIDN'T.
YOU CAN'T KIND OF DO BLOW.
- BUT THAT WAS SIX YEARS AGO
IN COLLEGE.
- AND I'M SUPPOSED TO BELIEVE
YOU'RE NOT ON ANYTHING NOW?
- I'M TOTALLY CLEAN.
- THEN WHY ARE YOU SO NERVOUS?
- BECAUSE I WASN'T EXPECTING
ON GETTING
THESE KINDS OF QUESTIONS.
I MEAN,
YOU SOUND LIKE A COP.
- I AM A COP.
I WORK FOR MIAMI
METRO HOMICIDE.
- LOOK, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
I CAME FOR A NANNY JOB.
I'M NOT, LIKE, PLANNING
TO KILL THE PRESIDENT.
- HARRISON NEEDS A NANNY AND DEB
INSISTED ON RUNNING POINT.
THE WAY IT'S GOING, ONLY MARY
POPPINS WOULD MAKE THE CUT.
- I DON'T CARE WHAT DOCTORS SAY.
I THINK IT'S IMPORTANT
FOR CHILDREN
TO EAT A LOT OF CHEESE.
- WELL, IF A CHILD'S CHOKING,
I JUST DO WHAT MY MAMA
ALWAYS DID.
YOU GET AHOLD OF IT
BY THE LEGS
AND YOU GIVE IT
A LITTLE KNUCKLE-SLAP.
- NO, I'VE NEVER HAD
MARTIAL ARTS TRAINING,
BUT I CAN SCREAM REAL LOUD.
- I HAVE A NURSING DEGREE
WITH AN EMPHASIS
ON INFANT/TODDLER GROWTH
AND DEVELOPMENT.
- WHY NOT WORK AT A HOSPITAL?
- WELL, I DID, BUT, UM,
THERE WERE BUDGET CUTS,
AND MY WARD WAS DOWNSIZED.
I LIVE ALONE.
I DON'T NEED A BIG SALARY,
SO A NANNY POSITION WOULD WORK
VERY WELL FOR ME.
HE'S TIRED.
MAY I?
I DON'T BITE.
- OKAY.
- HI.
OOH.
WHAT A LITTLE PRINCE YOU ARE.
MMM.
* BYE BABY BUNTING *
* DADDY'S GONE A HUNTING *
* GONE TO FIND A RABBIT SKIN *
* TO WRAP THE BABY BUNTING IN *
- AND THEN THERE WAS SONYA.
PRACTICALLY PERFECT
IN EVERY WAY.
- WELL, YOU HAVE MY NUMBER.
I'LL LOOK FORWARD
TO YOUR CALL.
AGAIN, MY CONDOLENCES
FOR YOUR LOSS.
- THANKS.
WE'LL BE IN TOUCH.
- BYE, PRINCE HARRY.
- SHE'S THE ONE.
- ARE YOU SURE YOU DON'T WANT
TO KEEP LOOKING, DEX?
- [sighs]
I JUST DON'T WANT TO LOSE HER.
PRINCE HARRY LIKES HER.
DITTO ME.
- THEN CALL HER.
DON'T FORGET,
YOU AND HARRISON--
- CRISIS COUNSELOR.
I WON'T FORGET.
- LOVE YOU, BRO.
- ME TOO.
EMPTINESS WASN'T
ALWAYS A PROBLEM.
I USED TO CHERISH IT.
BUT NOW IT FEELS LIKE
SOMETHING TO OVERCOME.
EMPTINESS IS ALL SHE HAS LEFT.
BOYD FOWLER.
DEPARTMENT OF SANITATION.
DIVISION OF DEAD ANIMAL PICKUP.
HOBBIES: SELF-IMPROVEMENT AND
STORING WOMEN IN FORMALDEHYDE.
I DON'T KNOW IF KILLING YOU
WILL FILL THE VOID,
BUT IT'S A PLACE TO START.
- WHAT'S THIS?
- ATM SURVEILLANCE VIDEO.
THE BANK SENT IT OVER.
THIS IS OUR SHOTGUN GUY.
- FRANCISCO ALFARO?
- YEAH.
IT'S WHAT HE LOOKED LIKE
WHEN HE HAD A FACE.
- WHEN WAS THIS TAKEN?
- TWO HOURS BEFORE
HE KILLED HIS WIFE
AND BLEW HIS OWN HEAD OFF.
TRYING TO GET CASH,
BUT HE KEEPS PUTTING IN
THE WRONG PIN NUMBER.
0371.
HIS WIFE'S BIRTHDAY.
- OUCH.
GOOD THING SHE'S DEAD.
HE NEVER WOULD HAVE
LIVED THAT DOWN.
- WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED
TO YOU GUYS?
- BATTLE SCARS.
WE HAD TO GET GHETTO
ON SOME DIRT-BAG
AT THE CLUB LAST NIGHT.
- YOU GUYS GOT
IN A BAR FIGHT?
- IT'S NOT WORTH
TALKING ABOUT.
- TRUE WARRIORS
ARE HUMBLE MEN.
- OH, PLEASE.
YOU GOT A REASON
TO BE HUMBLE.
YOU GOT FUCKED UP RUNNING
THE OTHER WAY.
- YOU'RE CONFUSING COWARDICE
WITH A TACTICAL RETREAT.
HERMANO, BACK ME UP HERE.
- YOU BACKED UP JUST FINE
ON YOUR OWN.
[laughter]
- OKAY, LET'S FOCUS
ON THE CASE, PEOPLE.
REMEMBER WHY WE'RE GETTING PAID.
- OKAY.
I'LL GO FIRST.
GUY OFFS HIS WIFE,
WANTS TO SKIP THE COUNTRY.
NEEDS CASH,
BUT HE'S SO WIGGED OUT,
HE CAN'T REMEMBER THE PIN.
GIVES UP, GOES HOME,
KILLS HIMSELF.
- ONLY PROBLEM WITH THAT
THEORY IS ALFARO
DOESN'T HAVE A MOTIVE
TO KILL HIS WIFE.
- MAYBE HE'S JUST SICK OF HER.
- OH, YEAH,
HE GOT SICK OF HER?
GOT SICK OF HER,
SO HE CUT OFF HER HEAD
AND PUT IT IN A PARK AND PUT
CANDLES ALL AROUND IT?
- YEAH.
HAVE YOU WATCHED THE VIDEO?
'CAUSE HE'S A LITTLE
FUCKING CRAZY.
- CRAZY DOES NOT EXPLAIN
WHY HE DOESN'T
HAVE A DROP OF BLOOD
ON HIS CLOTHES.
WHY DON'T YOU THINK
ABOUT THAT FOR A SECOND?
HOW DO YOU
CUT SOMEBODY'S HEAD OFF
AND NOT GET A DROP
OF BLOOD ON YOU?
WHAT'D HE DO?
WHAT, WEAR A BIB?
- AS MUCH FUN AS THIS IS,
WE'RE NOT GONNA HASH THIS
OUT IN THE ROOM.
- I WOULD LIKE TO RE-CANVASS
THE NEIGHBORHOOD
WHERE MRS. ALFARO'S BODY
WAS FOUND.
THERE ARE A LOT OF HOUSES
FACING THAT PARK.
SOMEBODY'S BOUND TO TALK.
- START TODAY.
- AND I THINK BATISTA
SHOULD BE THERE.
- HISPANIC NEIGHBORHOOD.
HISPANIC COP.
MIGHT RAISE THE COMFORT LEVEL.
LOOSEN TONGUES.
- I GET IT.
OKAY.
THE REST OF YOU,
STAY WITH THE CASE.
WORK YOUR LEADS.
THANKS.
- BEAUTIFUL.
- ANGEL?
- MM-HMM?
- JUST HOW BIG
WAS THIS FIGHT?
- LIKE I TOLD YOU THIS MORNING,
IT WAS A DISAGREEMENT
THAT GOT OUT OF HAND.
TOO MUCH BOOZE.
TOO MUCH TESTOSTERONE.
- [speaking Spanish]
UH...
YOU PUNCHED ANOTHER COP.
I MEAN, QUE PASO?
WHAT STARTED IT?
- WE HASHED IT OUT.
HOMBRE A HOMBRE.
IT'S SETTLED.
- PRETTY SURE HIS APPETITE'S
ABOUT THE SAME.
HE'S ALWAYS BEEN
KIND OF A MESSY EATER.
IT'S HARD TO TELL.
- HIS SLEEPING PATTERN?
- SAME.
UNFORTUNATELY, HE CRIES
ABOUT THREE TIMES A NIGHT
ON A GOOD NIGHT.
SO YOU'RE NOT SURPRISED THAT
HE'S ACTING PRETTY MUCH NORMAL?
- NO.
YOU AND HARRISON SUFFERED
A TERRIBLE TRAGEDY.
IT'S NO GETTING AROUND THAT,
BUT THERE IS SOMETHING
TO BE THANKFUL FOR.
- THANKFUL?
- YES.
HARRISON'S COGNITIVE ABILITIES
ARE REALLY JUST DEVELOPING.
- SO YOU'RE SAYING HE MIGHT
NOT BE AFFECTED
BY WHAT HE SAW?
- THERE'S JUST SIMPLY NO CHANCE
THAT HE WAS ABLE
TO COMPREHEND
WHAT WAS HAPPENING.
- [sighs]
I SAW SOMETHING PRETTY TRAUMATIC
WHEN I WAS THREE.
- HARRISON'S ONLY TEN MONTHS.
- IT AFFECTED ME A LOT.
YOU DON'T HAVE ANY IDEA.
- I'VE SEEN A LOT OF CHILDREN.
WE'LL KEEP AN EYE
ON HARRISON,
BUT I REALLY THINK YOUR SON
IS GONNA BE PERFECTLY FINE.
[Harrison crying]
- OOH.
HE WANTS HIS HEAD BACK.
AHH.
- CHILDREN HARRISON'S AGE
CAN EXHIBIT
WHAT MIGHT SEEM
LIKE VIOLENT BEHAVIOR,
BUT THEY'RE JUST
RELEASING ENERGY.
IT'S IMPORTANT NOT
TO READ INTO IT.
- I'LL TRY NOT TO.
- THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
YOU CAN DO RIGHT NOW
IS TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
FIND SOME TIME TO RELEASE
YOUR OWN ENERGY.
DO SOMETHING FOR DEXTER.
- DEXTER WILL.
- I HAVE NOTHING TO SAY.
I DIDN'T SEE NO ONE.
- WELL, IF YOU REMEMBER
ANYTHING
OR IF YOU HEAR ANYTHING--
- YES, MM-HMM.
I CALL YOU.
[speaking Spanish]
- [sighs]
- WE'RE NEVER GONNA HEAR
FROM HER.
ALL THIS NO TALKING
IS FUCKING FRUSTRATING.
- YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S FRUSTRATING?
9 DAYS, 13 HOURS.
- WHAT?
- SINCE WE--YOU KNOW?
JUST--
- YOU'RE COUNTING?
- I CAN'T HELP IT.
I HAVE AN INTERNAL CLOCK.
- WELL, UNPLUG IT.
- I'M JUST SAYING,
AT THIS POINT,
WE MIGHT AS WELL BE MARRIED.
- SHIT ON MY FACE.
YOU EVER WORDS LIKE
"WE" AND "MARRIED"
IN THE SAME FUCKING
SENTENCE AGAIN--
- WHOA.
- ANOTHER CASE
OF TEMPORARY BLINDNESS.
ANYTHING?
- THESE PEOPLE ARE
ALL AFRAID OF SOMETHING.
- YEAH, I'M GETTING THAT TOO.
- MAYBE THEY JUST DON'T WANT
TO GET INVOLVED.
- NO, I THINK IT'S MORE
THAN THAT.
IF THE KILLER'S DEAD,
WHAT ARE THEY AFRAID OF?
- I THOUGHT I COULD MAKE
SOME HEADWAY,
BUT THE REALITY IS THIS
IS A VENEZUELAN NEIGHBORHOOD.
- SO?
- I'M CUBAN.
OFFICER MANZON'S
FROM THIS NEIGHBORHOOD.
- MANZON?
- SHE'S A UNIFORM,
BUT SHE MIGHT
BE WORTH BRINGING IN.
- SHE THINKS THESE ARE
ABOUT RELIGIOUS MURDERS.
"SANTA MIERDA."
[laughter]
- THAT'S SANTA MUERTE.
IT'S "SAINT DEATH,"
NOT "SAINT SHIT."
AND MANZON MIGHT
BE ON TO SOMETHING.
MIGHT EXPLAIN
WHY NO ONE'S TALKING.
- SHUT UP.
- [chuckles]
[cell phone beeping]
[cell phone trilling]
- HELLO?
- HI, IT'S DEXTER.
- HI.
- YEAH, I DON'T KNOW
IF I MENTIONED,
BUT FOR HIS NAP,
HARRISON LIKES
THE PUPPY BLANKET
JUST TOUCHING HIS FACE.
- IT'S ON YOUR CHECKLIST.
UH, ITEM EIGHT UNDER
"SLEEP PREFERENCES."
- OKAY, GOOD.
HOW'S HE DOING?
- WE JUST READ
THE VERY HUNGRY CATERPILLAR
FOR THE SEVENTH TIME.
- DON'T WORRY.
HE USUALLY GETS SICK
OF IT AROUND THE 20TH READ.
I GOTTA GO.
[chuckles]
YEAH, YOU CALL ME
IF THERE'S ANYTHING.
THOUGHT HE'D NEVER SPOT ME.
- [chuckles]
SOME COINKYDINK, HUH?
YOU FIND ANY MORE
DEAD ANIMALS?
- LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE
WORKING ON SOMETHING.
- TASTES A LOT BETTER
THAN IT LOOKS.
- HAVE A SEAT.
- BOYD FOWLER.
- DARYL TUCKER.
- YOU WORK AROUND HERE?
- I JUST LOVE THE ARABICA.
ACTUALLY, I'M BETWEEN JOBS.
HENCE THE WANT ADS.
- WHAT KIND OF WORK
YOU LOOKING FOR?
- OH, NOT CHOOSY.
WHATEVER PAYS AND
GETS ME OUT OF THE HOUSE.
YOU LIKE WHAT YOU DO?
- I LOVE IT.
PROBABLY WOULDN'T THINK SO,
DRIVING AROUND,
PICKING UP DEAD ANIMALS.
- EH, BEATS WORKING
IN A CUBICLE.
YOU GET OUT IN THE FRESH AIR.
WELL, I GUESS MOST
OF THE TIME IT'S FRESH.
- [chuckles]
IT'S NOT BORING.
NEVER KNOW WHAT'S
AROUND THE NEXT BEND.
FULL OF SURPRISES.
YOU KNOW...
IF YOU'RE INTERESTED,
WE MIGHT HAVE
AN OPENING AT ANIMAL PICKUP.
- REALLY?
- YEAH, THERE AIN'T EXACTLY
A LINE EITHER.
[laughter]
YOU SHOULD TAKE A RIDE
WITH ME.
SEE IF YOU LIKE IT.
YOU GOT TO BE OKAY AROUND
DEAD THINGS THOUGH.
- I DON'T THINK
THAT'S A PROBLEM.
- GREAT.
TOMORROW MORNING,
8:00 SHARP.
- I WOULD HAVE SETTLED
FOR YOUR WORK SCHEDULE,
BUT THIS COULD BE BETTER.
ONLY 24 HOURS TO GET READY.
BOYD'S PATROL ROUTE.
NEED TO FIND A PLACE
WHERE WE CAN SPEND
SOME QUALITY TIME.
THERE.
AN OLD TOURIST WELCOME CENTER.
NOT VERY WELCOMING NOW.
TOTALLY ISOLATED.
THANK YOU, CITY OF MIAMI.
- YOU'RE GONNA KILL HIM
IN DAYLIGHT?
- DOESN'T MATTER OUT THIS FAR.
- IT'S STILL VERY RISKY.
WHAT IF SOMEONE COMES BY?
- THAT COULD ALSO HAPPEN
AT NIGHT.
- BUT IT'S A LOT LESS LIKELY.
YOU HAVE TO DO THIS RIGHT,
DEXTER.
IT'S IMPORTANT.
IT'S YOUR FIRST KILL SINCE--
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO TELL ME
HOW MUCH I NEED THIS.
- THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
- WHAT?
- THIS KILL WON'T PUT
EVERYTHING RIGHT.
IT WON'T BRING RITA BACK.
- IT MIGHT BRING ME BACK.
- IF YOU MAKE IT MEAN SO MUCH,
YOU'LL ONLY INVITE MISTAKES.
- I WON'T MAKE ANY MISTAKES.
I'M FOLLOWING THE CODE.
ARE YOU GONNA HELP ME OR NOT?
- I ONLY WANT
TO HELP YOU, DEX.
THIS IS A BIG ROOM.
I HOPE YOU BROUGHT
ENOUGH PLASTIC.
- IT FEELS GOOD GETTING
THE DETAILS RIGHT.
IT'S MORE THAN JUST PREPARING
A KILL ROOM.
IT'S LIKE I'M PUTTING
MY LIFE BACK IN ORDER.
AND IT'S ALMOST ENOUGH.
ALMOST.
- IF ANYONE KNOWS
ABOUT THESE MURDERS, IT'S FAUZI.
HE KNOWS EVERYBODY
IN THIS NEIGHBORHOOD.
- YOU REALLY GREW UP
AROUND HERE?
- YOU MAKE IT SOUND
LIKE A DISABILITY.
- I'M ASKING A QUESTION.
I'M NOT ABOUT
TO BURN A CROSS.
- I USED TO RIDE MY BIKE
AROUND THIS BLOCK.
THERE WAS THIS MEAN DOG
THAT LIVED THERE.
I MEAN, I USED TO PRAY
TO SAINT ANTHONY
TO MAKE ME INVISIBLE.
I NEVER GOT BIT.
- YOU THINK PRAYER
WAS THE REASON?
- YEAH.
THAT AND SOME HOMEMADE
PEPPER SPRAY.
- PODEMOS HABLAR CON FAUZI?
- POR QUE RAZON?
- POLICIA. ES IMPORTANTE.
POR FAVOR.
- UN MOMENTO.
- I WAS SURPRISED YOU CALLED.
THOUGHT YOU DIDN'T BELIEVE
WHAT I SAID AT THE CRIME SCENE.
- WHO SAYS I DO?
AT THIS POINT,
I CAN'T RULE ANYTHING OUT.
- WELL, BRINGING ME IN WAS
THE BEST MOVE, DETECTIVE.
YOU WON'T BE SORRY.
- ME LLAMO MANZON.
ESTE ES DETECTIVE MORGAN.
- ASK HIM IF HE'S HEARD
OF THE DEATHS
OF MR. AND MRS. ALFARO.
- HAS OIDO
DE LOS ASESINATOS?
- SI. UNA COSA TERRIBLE.
- THIS WAS FOUND
AT THE CRIME SCENE.
DID HE SELL IT TO MR. ALFARO?
- ESTO FUE ENCONTRADO
EN LA ESCENA.
SABIA USTED LO VENDE
AL SR. ALFARO?
- NO. EL ERA UN ESTRICTO
CATOLICO.
[continues in Spanish]
- HE SAYS ALFARO
WAS A STRICT CATHOLIC.
CAME INTO THE STORE NOW
AND THEN TO BUY SOME THINGS,
BUT HE WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
CAUGHT DEAD BACK HERE.
- DID HE SELL IT
TO ANYONE ELSE?
- SABIA SI USTED VENDIO
ESTO A ALGUIEN MAS?
- YOU NO SE QUIEN
COMPRA QUE.
[continues in Spanish]
- HE SAYS HE DOESN'T KEEP TRACK
OF WHO BUYS WHAT,
AND HE DOESN'T EVEN BELIEVE
IN THIS SHIT.
- IS THAT WHY HE HAS
THE TATTOO?
- I GOT DRUNK ONE NIGHT,
WOKE UP,
IT WAS THERE.
YOU TELL ME.
TE LLAMAS MANZON?
- SI. CIRA.
- CONO!
ERES LA HIJE DE ANDRES!
- HEY, HEY. [clicks tongue]
WE'RE DOING GREAT IN ENGLISH.
- YOU LIVE IN MIAMI.
WHY YOU NO LEARN SPANISH?
- BECAUSE ME TOO BUSY
MAKING A LIVING.
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE
YOU CAN TELL US?
ANYTHING THAT WILL HELP US
WITH THIS CASE?
- YO NO SE NADA.
- FAUZI'S HOLDING BACK.
I SHOULD HAVE TALKED
TO HIM BY MYSELF.
MIGHT HAVE BEEN
IN A MORE SHARING MOOD
WITH SOMEONE HE KNOWS.
- OH, YEAH?
MAYBE HE WOULD HAVE
SAID NOTHING
LIKE EVERYONE ELSE
IN THIS NEIGHBORHOOD.
- HEY, I KNOW YOU'RE
UP AGAINST IT,
BUT YOU MIGHT JUST WANT
TO TAKE A BREATH.
- [sighs]
WHY DON'T WE GIVE HIM THE NIGHT
TO STEW OVER THIS
AND THEN YOU COME
VISIT HIM TOMORROW ALONE?
- FINE.
- SONYA?
SONYA?
WHERE ARE THEY?
[cell phone dialing]
- HI, THIS IS SONYA.
LEAVE A MESSAGE.
- YEAH, IT'S DEXTER.
I JUST GOT BACK
AND YOU'RE NOT HERE
AND NOT ANSWERING YOUR CELL.
CALL ME NOW.
CAN'T HELP
BUT THINK THE WORST.
HARRISON'S BEEN STOLEN.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE LEFT HIM
WITH A STRANGER.
RITA WOULD HAVE NEVER
ALLOWED IT.
- HI.
FINALLY FALLEN ASLEEP.
- [sighs]
WHERE WERE YOU?
- WELL, HE WAS KEYED UP AFTER
HIS YO GABBA GABBA VIDEOS.
I THOUGHT SOME FRESH AIR
WOULD MAKE HIM DROWSY.
IT WORKED.
- YOU DIDN'T ANSWER YOUR CELL.
- WELL, I HAD MY HANDS FULL.
OH, I LEFT A NOTE
ON THE FRIDGE.
OH, I DIDN'T MEAN
TO WORRY YOU.
- NO, IT'S FINE.
I'M JUST...
[sighs]
I'M NOT USED TO CHECKING
THE FRIDGE FOR NOTES.
JUST MESSAGES
FROM OTHER SERIAL KILLERS.
- OH, I FEEL TERRIBLE.
- DON'T.
YOU WERE JUST DOING YOUR JOB.
HEY, I'M LUCKY TO HAVE YOU.
WE BOTH ARE.
[elevator bell dings]
- [chuckles]
[indistinct chatter]
[elevator bell dings]
- OH, A LITTLE COURTESY,
PLEASE.
[sighs]
THANKS.
YOU HITTING THE CLUB TONIGHT?
- NO.
HOME.
- OH, GOOD.
'CAUSE I WON'T BE THERE
TO WATCH YOUR BACK.
THERE COULD BE WINGMEN OUT THERE
LOOKING TO SETTLE THE SCORE.
- JUST DROP IT.
- WITH ALL DUE RESPECT,
THIS MAN IS A KNIGHT
IN SHINING ARMOR.
YOU SHOULD BE POLISHING
HIS LANCE.
- EXCUSE ME?
- I MEANT THAT
METAPHORICALLY.
NOT...HOW IT SOUNDED.
[elevator bell dings]
GOOD NIGHT.
- OKAY, I WANT TO KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT HAPPENED AT THE BAR.
- I TOLD YOU IT'S SETTLED.
[speaks Spanish]
- I'M NOT ASKING
AS YOUR WIFE.
- VINCE AND I WERE HAVING
DRINKS, KEEPING TO OURSELVES.
AND THEN OUT OF THE BLUE,
SERGEANT LOPEZ STARTS
TALKING SHIT.
- WHAT SHIT?
- YOU KNOW...SHIT.
HE WAS OUT OF LINE.
- SPECIFICS.
- [sighs]
HE ASKED IF YOU
AND I WERE MARRIED.
THEN HE SAID YOU WERE
A FINE PIECE OF ASS.
AND YOU WERE MY SUGAR MAMA.
- SUGAR MAMA?
- YEAH,
'CAUSE YOU'RE MY BOSS
AND YOUR PAYCHECK
HAS MORE ZEROS.
- DOES THAT REALLY
BOTHER YOU?
- A LITTLE.
DO YOU KNOW ANY GUYS
IT WOULDN'T BOTHER?
- SO YOU HIT HIM?
- NO, THERE'S MORE.
- MORE?
- YOU WANTED
TO KNOW EVERYTHING.
HE THEN SAID YOU GAVE
THE BEST BLOWJOBS IN MIAMI.
AND THEN I HIT HIM.
AND HE'S LUCKY
THAT'S ALL I DID.
- [sighs]
ANGEL, I'M A WOMAN
IN A POSITION OF POWER.
SOME MEN HAVE TROUBLE
DEALING WITH THAT,
SO THEY SPREAD
GARBAGE AROUND.
- I KNOW.
I KNOW.
AND I'M TRYING
TO WORK THROUGH IT.
- COULD YOU WORK THROUGH IT
WITHOUT THE BAR FIGHTS?
- I'LL KEEP THE BAR FIGHTS
AT A MINIMUM.
- HE SLEEPING?
- [sighs]
LIKE A BABY.
HOW WAS WORK?
- DIRE.
I'VE BEEN SADDLED WITH
THIS UNIFORM ON A HOMICIDE CASE
AND SHE'S DRIVING ME
APE-ASS CRAZY.
HOW'S THE NANNY?
- ASIDE FROM A LITTLE
MESSAGE HICCUP--
IT WAS TOTALLY MY FAULT--
SHE DID GREAT.
- I WONDER WHY
SHE LEFT IRELAND.
MAYBE SHE'S RUNNING
FROM SOMETHING.
- I DON'T KNOW, DEB.
MAYBE YOU BETTER CHECK
INTERPOL.
- WHAT ABOUT YOU?
WHAT'D YOU DO TODAY?
- NOT MUCH.
CODY CALLED.
HE WANTED ME TO SEND
MY RECIPE FOR PANCAKES.
- HOW ARE THEY?
- CODY SOUNDS...
HAPPIER.
ASTOR WOULDN'T COME
TO THE PHONE.
- SHE'LL COME AROUND, DEX.
- WELL, OTHER THAN THAT,
I RAN SOME ERRANDS.
- THAT'S GOOD.
GET BACK IN YOUR ROUTINE.
WHEN YOU LOSE SOMEONE CLOSE,
ROUTINE CAN BE A LADDER
THAT CAN HELP YOU CLIMB BACK
INTO SOME KIND OF NORMALCY.
- WHERE'D YOU HEAR THAT?
- I AM CAPABLE OF INDEPENDENT
THOUGHT, DEXTER.
OPRAH.
[laughter]
I WATCHED HER
WHEN I WAS LAID UP.
THAT'S GOOD.
KEEP GETTING BETTER, DEX.
- I'LL TRY.
YEAH, I'D LIKE TO REPORT
A DEAD ANIMAL.
UH, COUNTY ROAD 5,
MILE MARKER 31.
I'M NOT SURE.
I THINK IT WAS A GATOR.
IT WAS LONG AND SCALY.
YEAH.
THANK YOU.
IT'S ON BOYD'S CIRCUIT,
SO HE'LL GET THE CALL.
WHEN HE DOES, BOYD WILL
TAKE A LITTLE NAP
AND WAKE UP IN THE TOURIST
WELCOME CENTER,
BUT HE WON'T BE COLLECTING
ANY BROCHURES.
- WASN'T SURE YOU'D BE HERE.
- WOULDN'T MISS IT
FOR THE WORLD.
- HEY, I'M A SAFETY GUY.
- RIGHT.
NEVER BE TOO SAFE.
WHERE WE OFF TO FIRST?
- DEAD CAT ON LINDGREN.
BORING.
PRETTY NEIGHBORHOOD THOUGH.
LOT OF TROPHY WIVES
OUT JOGGING AT THIS HOUR.
- [chuckles]
THERE'S A BONUS.
- YOU HAVE TO EMBRACE THE NOW.
EVERY SECOND YOU WASTE
IS ONE MORE SECOND
YOU'LL NEVER GET BACK.
- EVER HEAR THIS GUY?
- WHEN I WAS SEARCHING
YOUR HOUSE.
- CHANGED MY LIFE.
REALLY HELPED ME SEE
WHAT'S IMPORTANT.
DO THE SAME FOR YOU.
EASE YOU THROUGH
THAT DIVORCE.
- DIVORCE?
- RING DENT.
- I DIDN'T WANT BOYD
TO KNOW THAT PART OF MY LIFE.
FOR A ROADKILL JANITOR,
HE DOESN'T MISS MUCH.
- HOPE IT'S NOT
A TOUCHY SUBJECT.
- NO, IT JUST DIDN'T WORK OUT.
- IF YOU NEED HELP
MOVING ON,
LISTEN TO THESE CDs.
- TAKE IT.
- TAKE IT NOW.
THAT'S THE MAIN IDEA.
- TAKE IT NOW?
- THERE'S MORE TO IT
THAN THAT,
BUT IT REALLY
MAKES A DIFFERENCE.
OF COURSE, YOU GOT TO KNOW
WHAT IT IS YOU WANT TO TAKE.
WHAT IS IT YOU WANT, DARYL?
- THAT'S KIND OF
A HARD QUESTION TO ANSWER.
- YES, IT IS.
BUT I REALLY THINK IT'S WHAT
WE'RE ON THIS EARTH TO FIND OUT.
- [chuckles]
JUSTIN BIEBER.
NOT THAT I KNOW WHO THAT IS.
- I KNOW WHO PURCHASED
THE SANTA MUERTE ICONS,
AND IT WASN'T
OUR DEAD HUSBAND.
- FAUZI TALKED?
- I WAS RIGHT.
HE WAS HOLDING BACK.
- WHAT'D YOU GET?
- NO NAMES,
BUT A DESCRIPTION.
TWO GUYS IN THEIR 30s,
STRONG ACCENTS,
POSSIBLY RECENT IMMIGRANTS
FROM VENEZUELA.
CRIMINAL TYPES.
THOSE WERE HIS WORDS.
AND BIG INTO SANTA MUERTE.
- WHAT IF ALFARO
ISN'T FREAKED OUT
BECAUSE HE JUST MURDERED
HIS WIFE?
WHAT IF HE'S FREAKED OUT BECAUSE
SOMEONE'S GOT HIS WIFE?
- AND THEY'LL KILL HER UNLESS
HE PAYS CASH.
- THIS ISN'T DRUG RELATED.
MAYBE SHE WAS FUCKING
HELD HOSTAGE FOR RANSOM.
YOU THINK FAUZI SPILLED
EVERYTHING HE KNOWS?
- HE'S BEEN ASKING
AROUND THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
THINKS HE CAN DIG UP
SOME MORE.
- WELL,
LET'S FUCKING FIND OUT.
- SOMETIMES IT GETS SO HOT,
THESE THINGS
ACTUALLY START FRYING.
AND YOU GOT TO--
YOU GOT TO SCRAPE 'EM OFF
LIKE DINER FOOD.
- TWO HOURS AND NO CALL
ABOUT MY GATOR.
THEY MUST HAVE SENT
SOMEONE ELSE.
- GOD ALMIGHTY.
THAT STINK GETS
IN YOUR SOUL.
- WHICH MEANS THIS KILL
IS DEAD.
- MAN, YOU GOT A NOSE OF STEEL.
YOU'RE MADE FOR THIS JOB.
- [chuckles]
NOW I'M STUCK WITH BOYD.
- [grunts]
- SO MUCH FOR GETTING
MY LIFE BACK.
- IT'S ALMOST LUNCH TIME.
I USUALLY EAT AT HOME
BY MYSELF,
BUT THERE'S A CHINESE PLACE
NOT TOO FAR.
[cell phone rings]
HANG ON.
[sighs]
BOYD.
- MAYBE THE UNIVERSE
IS SHOWING MERCY ON ME.
- WHAT'S THE LOCATION?
I'M ON IT.
- WHAT'S UP?
- DEAD GATOR
OUT ON COUNTY FIVE.
FIRST PROMISING THING ALL DAY.
BUT IF YOU'RE STARVING,
WE CAN PUSH IT
TILL AFTER LUNCH.
- I'M GOOD.
- THEN LET'S RUMBLE.
GATOR RUNS CAN GET HAIRY.
YOU GOT TO BE ON YOUR TOES.
- HAIRY HOW?
- CAN'T ALWAYS TELL
IF THEY'RE REALLY DEAD.
- YIKES.
- DON'T WORRY.
LIKE I SAID...
I'M A SAFETY GUY.
- MUST BE AT LUNCH.
- HELLO?
HELLO?
SHIT.
[guns click]
- DETECTIVE.
- CALL IT IN.
DO IT.
- THIS IS OFFICER MANZON.
- MILE MARKER SHOULD
BE RIGHT AROUND HERE.
BE CAREFUL.
SUCKER COULD BE ANYWHERE.
YOU REALLY DON'T
WANT TO STEP ON IT.
- FINALLY...
IT'S RIGHT.
- [grunts]
[tranquilizer gun fires]
[grunts]
- [slurring]
SHIT.
[siren wails]
[electronic beeping]
WHERE AM I?
- ON YOUR WAY
TO COUNTY MEDICAL.
YOU KNOW WHAT CITY
YOU'RE IN?
- MIAMI.
- WHAT DAY IS IT?
- WEDNESDAY.
WHAT HAPPENED TO ME?
- A MOTORIST SPOTTED YOU LYING
ON THE SIDE OF THE ROAD,
CALLED 911.
SEEMS THIS GUY
SHOT YOU WITH A TRANQ DART.
BOYS HAVE AN ARGUMENT
OR SOMETHING?
- NO. NO.
WENT OFF BY ACCIDENT.
- CRAZY ASSHOLE, YOU WERE
SUPPOSED TO SHOOT THE GATOR.
- YOU GOT IN MY WAY,
YOU FUCKING NUMBSKULL.
- SO WHAT'S YOUR EXCUSE?
- HUH?
- WHY WERE YOU UNCONSCIOUS?
- THEY MUST NOT HAVE FOUND
MY NEEDLE.
- I GUESS I WAS JUST SO UPSET
THAT I PASSED OUT.
- THERE'S ONE PIECE
OF GOOD LUCK.
- I REALLY NEED
TO GET BACK TO MY TRUCK.
- YEAH, SORRY.
I CAN'T LET YOU JUMP OUT
OF A MOVING AMBULANCE.
WE'LL BE THERE SOON.
NEED TO GET YOU BOTH
CHECKED OVER.
[siren wails]
- GOT HIM.
- DROP IT.
- LET'S GO.
- LET'S GO ON THREE.
[electronic beeping]
- CHART.
I'M DR. LORRE.
I UNDERSTAND YOU SUFFERED
A LOSS OF CONSCIOUSNESS.
- THAT'S WHAT I'M TOLD.
- THAT EVER HAPPEN BEFORE?
- UM...FIRST TIME.
- YOU HAVE ANY HISTORY
OF HEADACHES,
DIZZINESS, BLURRED VISION?
- UH-UH.
- HYPOGLYCEMIA?
- NOT THAT I KNOW OF.
- OKAY.
WE'RE GONNA RUN
A CHEM PROFILE
AND CHECK YOUR GLUCOSE LEVELS
FOR POSSIBLE DEHYDRATION.
WE'LL FOLLOW UP
WITH A TOX SCREEN.
SEE IF ANYTHING'S
IN YOUR SYSTEM.
- I'LL BE RIGHT BACK
TO DRAW YOUR BLOOD.
JUST LIE STILL.
[overlapping chatter]
- [muttering]
- HE'S IN THERE, OKAY.
JUST GIVE HIM ASPIRIN.
NO PAINKILLERS.
- I'M SORRY, DOCTOR.
I DIDN'T KNOW
ABOUT HIS ADDICTION.
- WELL, YOU GOT TO CHECK THE
PATIENT'S RECORDS HERE, HE'S--
FIFTH TIME HE'S BEEN
IN THE E.R. THIS YEAR.
THIS IS HIS FIFTH ACCIDENT.
- IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
- ALL RIGHT.
[indistinct radio chatter]
- [sighs]
ANOTHER HEAD?
AND I WAS IN
SUCH A GOOD MOOD.
- IT'S MY FAULT.
I GOT HIM KILLED.
- FUCK THAT.
YOU DIDN'T CUT HIS HEAD OFF.
- THEY DID THIS BECAUSE
HE STARTED TALKING TO ME.
IF I HADN'T COME BACK HERE,
FAUZI WOULD STILL BE ALIVE.
- IT WAS MY CALL.
WE'RE IN THIS TOGETHER.
AND WE'RE CLOSER TO CATCHING HIM
BECAUSE OF YOU, OKAY?
YOU DID GOOD.
- LOOKS LIKE, UH...
THE SAME TREATMENT
AS OUR OTHER, UH, HEAD CASE.
[chuckles]
EYES AND TONGUE
HAVE BEEN EXCISED.
DAMN, DON'T PEOPLE JUST SHOOT
EACH OTHER ANYMORE?
[cell phone rings]
- EXCUSE ME A SEC.
[keypad tone]
HEY, THANKS
FOR CALLING ME BACK.
- NO PROB.
SORRY IT TOOK SO LONG.
WE'RE UP TO OUR NECKS
ON THIS TRINITY THING.
- YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I WANT
TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
I THINK I MAY HAVE
A LEAD ON KYLE BUTLER.
- KYLE BUTLER?
- YEAH, YOU KNOW,
THE GUY WHO WAS HANGING AROUND
WITH ARTHUR MITCHELL?
- YEAH, I KNOW WHO HE IS.
JUST DIDN'T KNOW YOU PEOPLE
WERE WORKING THIS.
- I'M SORT OF, UH,
FLYING OFF THE RECORD.
LISTEN.
IS THERE ANY CHANCE I COULD TALK
TO THE MITCHELL FAMILY?
- THE MITCHELLS
ARE IN A SAFE HOUSE.
FIRST STOP BEFORE
WITNESS PROTECTION.
- JUST WANT TO SHOW THEM
A PHOTO.
TAKE FIVE MINUTES.
- GIVE ME THE PHOTO.
I'LL SHOW IT TO THEM.
- AHH, IT'S TOO SENSITIVE.
IF I'M WRONG,
IT COULD MEAN MY ASS.
COME ON...
RAY, AS A FRIEND.
- I'LL SEE WHAT I CAN DO,
BUT NO PROMISES.
- THANKS.
LET ME KNOW.
[keypad tone]
- TAKE IT.
NOW, BEFORE YOU CAN
TAKE ANYTHING...
- WHAT THE FUCK?
- YOU HAVE TO KNOW
WHAT IT IS YOU WANT.
MAY SOUND EASY, BUT YOU
CAN'T KNOW WHAT YOU WANT
UNLESS YOU KNOW YOURSELF.
BUT IF YOU WANT SOMETHING,
THERE'S ONLY ONE OPTION.
TAKE IT.
YOU WANT THAT PROMOTION?
WELL, THEN TAKE IT.
YOU WANT THAT NEW CAR,
THAT HOUSE?
TAKE IT.
- [grunts]
THAT COULD HAVE GONE SMOOTHER.
COULD HAVE ALSO GONE WORSE.
LEAST HE'S DOWN.
[keypad tones]
[cell phone trilling]
- HELLO?
- HI, IT'S DEXTER.
WANTED TO TELL YOU
THAT I'M GONNA
BE A LITTLE LATER
THAN I EXPECTED.
- IT'S NO PROBLEM.
- MY SISTER SHOULD
BE THERE ANY MINUTE THOUGH.
- ACTUALLY, SHE PHONED TOO.
SHE'S TIED UP AT WORK.
- OH.
- IT'S OKAY.
I DON'T MIND STAYING LATE.
I--I LIKE WATCHING HIM SLEEP.
- YOU'RE A LIFESAVER.
- I WAS GONNA CALL YOU.
- IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
- HE TOOK HIS FIRST STEP.
AT LEAST I THINK
IT WAS HIS FIRST.
- HE DID?
- IT WAS ONLY ONE STEP,
BUT YOU COULD TELL
HE WAS REALLY PROUD
OF HIMSELF.
- THAT'S AMAZING.
- I MANAGED
TO GET A SHOT FOR YOU.
CHECK YOUR EMAIL.
- THANKS.
I'LL CALL YOU WHEN
I'M ON MY WAY HOME.
[keypad tones]
MY SON IS WALKING...
LIKE A NORMAL LITTLE BOY.
[sighs]
- I'M ON MY WAY THERE
RIGHT NOW.
JUST START TROLLING
FOR EYEWITNESSES.
MAYBE WE'LL CATCH A BREAK.
MAYBE SOMEONE
SAW SOMETHING, OKAY?
- LIEUTENANT LAGUERTA?
- YES?
- JIM MCCOURT,
INTERNAL AFFAIRS.
I WONDER IF I COULD HAVE
A WORD WITH YOU IN PRIVATE?
- OF COURSE.
SO...WHAT'S THIS ABOUT?
- WELL, THIS IS REALLY
A COURTESY CALL.
WE'RE ABOUT TO LAUNCH
A FORMAL INVESTIGATION
INTO ONE OF YOUR DETECTIVES--
A...ANGEL BATISTA.
I UNDERSTAND
HE'S YOUR HUSBAND.
- YES.
YES, HE IS.
- APPARENTLY, HE HAD
A PHYSICAL ALTERCATION
WITH ONE OF HIS
FELLOW OFFICERS--
A SERGEANT LOPEZ.
- I WAS UNDER THE IMPRESSION
THE MATTER WAS SETTLED.
- OH, FAR FROM IT.
LOPEZ COLLAPSED
WHILE ON DUTY TODAY.
HE'S BEEN HOSPITALIZED
WITH INTERNAL BLEEDING.
- MY GOD.
- WE BELIEVE
THAT HE'LL PULL THROUGH,
BUT HE'S FILED CHARGES.
SOMETHING ELSE YOU
SHOULD BE AWARE OF:
WE HAVE TWO EYEWITNESSES
WHO CLAIM THAT THEY SAW BATISTA
KICK SERGEANT LOPEZ
WHILE ON THE GROUND.
NOW, IF THAT IS TRUE,
THAT IS ASSAULT
WITH A DEADLY WEAPON
AND HE COULD NOT ONLY
LOSE HIS JOB...
HE COULD SERVE TIME.
- HAD TO BORROW THIS FROM YOU.
I HOPE YOU DON'T MIND.
- WHAT THE HELL?
- NORMALLY,
I BRING MY OWN PLASTIC,
BUT...
I HAD TO...
IMPROVISE.
- [grunts]
LET ME THE FUCK OUT OF HERE.
- I BET YOU'VE HEARD
THAT BEFORE--
"LET ME OUT OF HERE"--FROM
ALL THE WOMEN YOU'VE KILLED.
I WISH YOU COULD SEE
THE ROOM I SET UP FOR YOU.
BUT YOU FUCKED
EVERYTHING UP, BOYD.
ALL THOSE PICTURES I TOOK
OF THE WOMEN YOU KILLED.
IT'S A SHAME YOU'LL NEVER
GET TO SEE THEM.
I'LL JUST HAVE TO PAINT
A WORD-PICTURE FOR YOU INSTEAD.
THEY WERE YOUNG.
JUST STARTING THEIR LIVES.
NOW THEY'RE FLOATING
IN FORMALDEHYDE
AND STUFFED INTO BARRELS STREWN
AROUND A SWAMP.
- WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
- JUST A FELLOW TRAVELER
WHO...
ALSO LIKES TO PICK UP
DEAD ANIMALS.
- I DID 'EM A FAVOR.
THEY WERE ALL SUFFERING
AND I PUT 'EM
OUT OF THEIR MISERY.
- YEAH, YOU'LL BE DOING
ONE MORE FAVOR TONIGHT.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- I'VE RECENTLY SUFFERED
A LOSS.
MY WIFE...
WAS MURDERED
BY SOMEONE LIKE YOU.
SOMEONE LIKE ME.
IT TURNED MY LIFE UPSIDE DOWN.
- WHY IS IT MY PROBLEM?
- BECAUSE YOU'RE THE START
OF MY HEALING PROCESS.
- I KNEW YOU WERE FUCKED UP
THE MINUTE
I LAID EYES ON YOU.
- I WAS FUCKED UP LONG
BEFORE THAT.
- YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE GETTING INTO.
- REMEMBER IN THE TRUCK
YOU ASKED ME WHAT I WANT?
I WANT MY WIFE BACK...
BUT THIS WILL HAVE TO DO.
- [grunts and coughs]
- NO CHURCH BELLS.
NO HALLELUJAH CHORUS.
NOTHING FEELS DIFFERENT.
IF ANYTHING, I'M EMPTIER.
[scuffling]
IT'S OKAY.
I'M NOT GONNA HURT YOU.
HERE.
NO, DON'T.
DON'T.
STOP.
NO.
SHE SAW EVERYTHING.
- [groans]
- SHE SAW...ME.