- PREVIOUSLY ON DEXTER...
- YOU WERE FACE-TO-FACE
WITH CARLOS FUENTES, RIGHT?
[gunshot]
SO THAT MEANS HE KNOWS
THAT WE'RE ONTO HIM.
TELL ME WHY THEY WOULD EVER
RETURN TO THIS CLUB.
- YOU HAVE ONE MORE NIGHT
AT CLUB MAYAN.
MAKE SOMETHING HAPPEN.
- THIS IS YASMIN ARAGON.
IF WE AGREE TO DROP
HER DRUG CHARGES,
SHE THINKS SHE CAN GET THE
FUENTES BROTHERS IN THE CLUB.
- HEY.
- I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT WANT
A DEBRIEFING
BEFORE WE HIT CLUB MAYAN.
- UM, IT'S SORT OF NOT
A GOOD TIME.
THIS IS STAN LIDDY.
- YOU ARE BONING
OUR TARGET'S SISTER?
- JUST TELL ME WHAT YOU FOUND
OUT ON DEXTER MORGAN.
- YOU FUCKED
EVERYTHING UP, BOYD.
BOYD FOWLER.
HOBBIES--
SELF-IMPROVEMENT...
- TAKE IT!
- AND STORING WOMEN
IN FORMALDEHYDE.
EVERY ONE OF THESE BARRELS
HAS A BODY IN IT.
- BOYD WASN'T THE ONLY ONE
WHO DID THIS TO ME.
THERE WERE OTHERS.
I SHOT ONE OF THEM.
DEXTER, WHAT DO I DO?
- THAT LAST FUCKING BITCH
IS ALIVE.
THEY'RE GONNA FIND YOU.
- SOME EXPERIENCES ARE SO BIG
THEY CHANGE YOUR DNA.
- I'M GONNA HAVE TO FIND
THE REST OF THEM,
BECAUSE THAT'S THE ONLY WAY THAT
I CAN FEEL THIS PEACE AGAIN.
- I CAN'T GET REVENGE
FOR RITA'S DEATH,
BUT I CAN HELP LUMEN AVENGE
WHAT WAS DONE TO HER.
HOW MANY MORE WERE THERE?
[quirky music]
* *
- IT'S BEEN OVER A MONTH
SINCE I FREED LUMEN FROM BOYD'S,
BUT SHE'S STILL
RELIVING IT EVERY DAY.
HEY.
I BROUGHT FOOD.
- OH.
- HAVE YOU EATEN?
- I ATE THIS MORNING.
- WELL, NOW IT'S NIGHT.
EAT SOME MORE.
- YOU'RE VERY...CONTROLLING.
- WHEN I NEED TO BE.
SO WHAT ELSE?
DETAILS WOULD HELP.
- BESIDES THE ONES
THAT WE'VE ALREADY...
TAKEN CARE OF...
THERE WAS WATCH GUY.
- "WATCH GUY"?
- I WOULD BE TIED
TO A CHAIR...
BLINDFOLDED.
SOMETIMES I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
IF HE WAS THERE
UNTIL I'D HEAR THIS WATCH
BY MY EAR.
AND THEN HE'D LEAN IN
AND WHISPER,
"TICK, TICK, TICK.
THAT'S THE SOUND OF YOUR LIFE
RUNNING OUT."
- OKAY.
ANYONE ELSE?
- SUIT AND TIE.
HE'D TAKE OFF HIS JACKET
AND FOLD IT...
VERY CAREFULLY
AND THEN LAY IT ON A CHAIR,
LIKE HE DIDN'T WANT
TO MESS IT UP.
SUIT GUY I'D KNOW.
HE ALWAYS TOOK
THE BLINDFOLD OFF.
I GUESS HE THOUGHT
I'D BE DEAD SOON.
- HE WAS WRONG.
- [speaking Spanish]
SI?
[flies buzzing]
- SO WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
HOW DO WE FIND THEM?
- I'M NOT SURE "WE" IS
THE OPERATING WORD HERE.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WE'RE DOING THIS TOGETHER.
- LUMEN, WHAT I DO,
I DO ALONE.
I DON'T NEED A PARTNER.
I SAID I'D HELP YOU,
BUT--
- FINE.
FORGET IT.
- FORGET IT?
- THERE'S NO POINT TO IT, THEN.
- YOU WANT THESE MEN
BROUGHT TO JUSTICE?
- YEAH, AND I CAN'T GO
TO THE COPS BECAUSE OF YOU.
SO YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO BE
A LITTLE FLEXIBLE HERE.
I WANT TO BE A PART OF THIS.
- WE'LL SEE.
[indistinct chatter]
- [speaking Spanish]
GRACIAS.
[truck engine turns]
- I NEED TO GET HOME
TO HARRISON.
- RIGHT.
THE OTHER PART OF YOUR LIFE.
- THERE IS NO OTHER PART
TO LUMEN'S LIFE.
THIS IS ALL SHE HAS.
EVEN SO, I CAN'T BRING HER
INTO MY WORLD.
THERE'S NO PLACE FOR HER.
- DEXTER?
THANK YOU.
- I FEEL LIKE I'M DROPPING OFF
MY PROM DATE...
EXCEPT THIS IS MY HOUSE,
AND MY WIFE IS DEAD,
AND I HAVE NO IDEA WHERE LUMEN
FITS INTO MY WORLD,
AND THIS IS ALL SO WEIRD...
EXACTLY LIKE MY PROM.
- OUR LEVEL OF NATIONAL DEBT
IS UNSUSTAINABLE.
[continues indistinctly]
...WHERE INDEPENDENT PRODUCERS
ARE WEIGHED DOWN
BY PARASITIC NON-PRODUCERS,
A DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENT
AND A DEMOCRATIC CONGRESS.
[tires screech, crash]
[musical toy playing lullaby]
* *
- YOU'RE JUST IN TIME.
[door closes]
- HEY, GOOD NIGHT, BUDDY.
- SAINT BRIGID,
CIRCLE US WITH YOUR LIGHT
SO THAT NO DARKNESS
SHALL OVERCOME OUR WORLD.
SLEEP WELL, LITTLE ONE.
- THAT'S EITHER A SAINT
OR THE MOST BORING
ACTION FIGURE I'VE EVER SEEN.
IS THAT YOURS?
- IT'S SAINT BRIGID.
[sighs]
TO WATCH OVER YOU
WHILE YOU SLEEP.
GOOD NIGHT.
- GOOD NIGHT.
HE DOESN'T NEED SAINT BRIGID.
HE HAS FATHER DEXTER.
- WHY ARE YOU UP SO EARLY?
- GYM.
- BUT HOW ABOUT IT?
YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, WE DON'T HAVE
TO LIVE HERE.
WE COULD GET
A NEW PLACE TOGETHER.
[cell phone rings]
- [scoffs]
[keypad tone]
MORGAN.
I'M HOMICIDE.
I DON'T DO TRAFFIC ACCIDENTS.
WOW.
UH, TEXT ME THE ADDRESS.
[keypad tone]
- WHAT'S UP?
- DEAD PEOPLE.
YOU'RE GONNA GET THE SAME CALL.
WE'RE ALL GETTING CALLED IN.
- WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL THEM
I'M HERE?
- BECAUSE I'M NOT HERE.
BASICALLY, NOBODY KNOWS
WE'RE SEEING EACH OTHER.
I JUST WANT TO KEEP IT
THAT WAY.
- WOW, BABY.
YOU SAY THE SWEETEST THINGS.
CAN WE AT LEAST DRIVE
IN TOGETHER?
- YEAH, AND THEN WE'LL GO
TO DISNEY WORLD,
AND WE'LL RIDE ALL
THE ROLLER COASTERS,
AND WE'LL HOLD HANDS.
- I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS.
[siren wails]
[indistinct chatter]
- WHATEVER IT IS...
IT'S BIG.
- DEXTER.
- HEY, SERGEANT.
WHAT HAVE WE GOT?
- YOU HAVEN'T BEEN LISTENING
TO THE NEWS?
- UH, WEATHER CHANNEL.
HIGH-PRESSURE SYSTEM
COMING IN.
- WHAT HAVE WE GOT?
[indistinct radio chatter]
WE GOT HER...
AND HER...
AND HER.
- THE GIRLS IN THE BARRELS--
HOW COULD THIS BE?
SOMEONE TRIED TO MOVE THEM.
WHERE'S THE DRIVER?
- THAT'S WHAT WE'RE TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT.
HE TOOK OFF.
GO DO YOUR THING.
- IT'S THE BLOOD GUY,
BUT WE GOT NO BLOOD.
- WE DON'T KNOW WHAT WE'VE GOT.
- YEAH, WHAT IS THIS GUNK?
- IT'S FORMALIN,
LIQUID FORMALDEHYDE.
- WHY?
- AN EMBALMING AGENT.
BECAUSE IT WAS ONLY
APPLIED TOPICALLY,
THE INTERNAL ORGANS
OF THE CADAVERS
CONTINUED TO PUTREFY AND LEAK
OUT OF THE VARIOUS
BODILY ORIFICES,
BECOMING CONGEALED
ONCE THEY CAME IN CONTACT
WITH THE FORMALIN.
THAT'S WHAT'S ON YOUR SHOE--
CONGEALED ORGAN.
- WHAT KIND OF SICK FUCK
ARE WE DEALING WITH?
- I'M JUST THE BLOOD GUY.
- WE'VE GOT FIVE VICTIMS--
ALL FEMALE, ALL BLONDE,
ALL BETWEEN THE AGES
OF 20 AND 35, I'M GUESSING.
THEY'RE COVERED IN BRUISES,
CONTUSIONS, WHIP MARKS.
LOOKS LIKE THEY WENT THROUGH
SOME SPECIAL KIND OF HELL.
WE'LL GET FINGERPRINTS OFF THEM
ONCE WE GET 'EM
TO THE M.E.'S OFFICE.
- I HEARD
THE DRIVER TOOK OFF.
- YEAH, WE'VE GOT THE GUY
THAT HIT HIM.
HE WAS DRUNK
OFF HIS FREAKING ASS.
HE SAID HE SAW SOME GUY
JUMP OUT AND START RUNNING,
BUT THAT'S AS DETAILED
AS HIS DESCRIPTION GETS--
"SOME GUY."
- THAT MEANS HE'S STILL MINE
TO FIND...
OR VINCE MASUKA'S.
HEY.
- HEY, DEX.
THAT'S SOME
PRETTY CRAZY SHIT, HUH?
- YEAH, CRAZY SHIT.
WHAT DO YOU GOT?
- UH...
ONE MEN'S SUIT JACKET,
SIZE 40.
- DID YOU FOLD IT,
OR WAS IT ALREADY LIKE THAT?
- I BAGGED IT AS I FOUND IT.
I ALSO GOT
FINGERPRINTS GALORE...
- EXCELLENT.
- EXCEPT
FOR THE STEERING WHEEL.
SOMEBODY GAVE IT A QUICK WIPE.
I'LL GET THE VEHICLE BACK
TO THE LAB,
AND WE'LL GIVE IT
A MORE THOROUGH GOING-OVER.
- RIGHT.
SO MUCH FOR KEEPING
MY LIVES SEPARATE.
[cell phone vibrates]
[keypad tone]
- YEAH, WHAT'S UP?
- WHAT YOU DOING, BOY?
SLEEPING LATE?
YOUR BUDDY DEXTER MORGAN--
YOU ASKED ME
TO KEEP AN EYE ON HIM.
- YEAH?
AND?
- WELL, HE'S GOT SOME CUTIE
UP AT HIS HOUSE.
HE EVEN TOOK DOWN
THE "FOR SALE" SIGN.
- WHAT'S THIS GIRL LOOK LIKE?
- BLONDE, AVERAGE HEIGHT,
LATE 20s.
- SLIM, PRETTY?
- THAT'D BE HER.
- FIND OUT WHO SHE IS.
- YOU BETCHA.
[keypad tone]
- COME HERE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- I SAW THE NEWS.
I KNEW WHAT IT WAS.
I HAD TO COME.
- NO, YOU DIDN'T HAVE
TO COME.
- DEXTER, I WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE ONE OF THOSE GIRLS.
- LOOK, IT'S NOT SAFE
FOR YOU HERE.
THEY COULD BE WATCHING.
- WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
- IT MEANS THEY'RE ON THE RUN.
YOU NEED TO GO.
- WILL YOU GIVE ME--
THANK YOU.
SHIT A BRICK
AND FUCK ME WITH IT.
YOU'RE NEVER GONNA GUESS
WHO THIS TRUCK IS REGISTERED TO.
JORDAN CHASE.
- JORDAN CHASE
IS A VERY SMART GUY.
HIS FIRST BOOK
MADE ME REALIZE
HOW I'D BEEN PUTTING
ALL THESE LIMITATIONS ON MYSELF.
I MEAN, I'VE LISTENED
TO ALL HIS CDs.
- SO DID BOYD FOWLER.
YOU THINK JORDAN COULD HAVE BEEN
DRIVING THAT TRUCK?
- WHAT?
NO WAY.
FIRST OFF,
THAT JACKET IS NICE,
BUT NOT THAT NICE.
JORDAN WEARS NOTHING
BUT THE BEST.
THAT'S PART OF HIS THING.
IF YOU THINK
YOU DESERVE SOMETHING,
THEN TAKE IT.
[sighs]
I'VE LIFTED
TWO DOZEN FINGERPRINTS,
AND THEY ALL SEEM TO BELONG
TO THE SAME PERSON.
[sighs]
AND WHOEVER THEY BELONG TO,
HE'S NOT IN THE AFIS DATABASE.
DEAD END.
OOH, A HAIR.
AND ANOTHER ONE.
[chuckles]
- IT'S NOT OFTEN I'M IN
COMPETITION WITH MY OWN PEOPLE,
BUT GETTING THE IDENTITY
OF THE DRIVER OF THE TRUCK
AND GETTING TO HIM
BEFORE THEY DO
IS THE ONLY WAY I CAN GIVE LUMEN
WHAT I PROMISED.
- ALL I GET
IS A FUCKING COMPUTER.
I CAN ORDER JORDAN CHASE BOOKS.
I CAN ORDER JORDAN CHASE CDs,
BUT I CAN'T TALK
TO AN ACTUAL PERSON.
- JORDAN CHASE IS A REALLY
POPULAR MAN, YOU KNOW?
HE TRAVELS THE WORLD GIVING HIS
LITTLE TOUCHY-FEELY SEMINARS.
HE'S PROBABLY NOT EVEN
IN MIAMI RIGHT NOW.
- I'VE LEFT MESSAGES
ALL OVER.
IF I DON'T HEAR BACK SOON,
I'M GONNA KICK THEIR DOOR IN.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
ANYTHING?
- YEAH, WE'VE I.D.'D TWO
OF THE GIRLS
OFF THEIR FINGERPRINTS.
ONE WAS A SCHOOLTEACHER
FROM WISCONSIN.
SHE CAME OUT HERE ON VACATION
TWO YEARS AGO--
NEVER HEARD FROM AGAIN.
THE OTHER ONE WORKED ON A CRUISE
SHIP THAT WAS DOCKED HERE.
SHE DISAPPEARED
JUST OVER A YEAR AGO.
- WOW.
- YEAH, THESE WERE GOOD GIRLS,
YOU KNOW?
ONE WAS 26.
ONE WAS 29.
- NOTHING ON THE OTHER THREE?
- NO, I'M GOING THROUGH
THE MISSING-PERSON DATABASES,
PUT THEIR
PHOTOGRAPHS OUT THERE.
- DNA?
- IT'S BEING RUN NOW.
LOOKING FOR DIRECT HITS
AND FAMILIAL HITS.
- LISTEN...
I HEARD ABOUT THIS TWO-BEDROOM
PLACE ON BRICKELL--
UPPER UNIT,
RIGHT ON THE WATER.
THOUGHT WE COULD TAKE A LOOK.
- THIS IS NOT
A WORKPLACE CONVERSATION,
SO PLEASE JUST SHUT UP.
- ALL I'M SAYING IS,
IS THIS PLACE IS GOING FAST.
- LISTEN, PLEASE,
JUST NOT HERE.
- YOU TWO...
NOW.
- SHIT.
THINK SHE KNOWS ABOUT US?
IS THIS ABOUT--
- THE SANTA MUERTE CASE.
- OH.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS DEAD.
- WELL, NOW IT'S ALIVE, BARELY.
- YASMIN ARAGON, THE ASSOCIATE
OF THE FUENTES BROTHERS
THAT SERGEANT BATISTA
IDENTIFIED,
HAS ASSURED US
THAT SHE WILL BRING
CARLOS AND MARCO INTO CLUB MAYAN
TOMORROW NIGHT.
- SO WE'RE ON?
- WE ARE ON.
- I AM PERSONALLY OVERSEEING
THIS OPERATION.
WE CAN'T RISK WORD LEAKING OUT
TO THE FUENTES,
SO IT'S STRICTLY
ON A NEED-TO-KNOW BASIS.
RATHER THAN FLOODING
THE CLUB WITH POLICE PERSONNEL,
WE WILL BE PERFORMING
A SMALL SURGICAL OPERATION.
WE WILL TAKE THE BROTHERS
INTO CUSTODY
BEFORE THEY GET INTO THE CLUB.
- DETECTIVE MORGAN,
YOU'LL BE WITH ME
IN THE SURVEILLANCE VAN.
DETECTIVE QUINN,
WE'RE GONNA POST YOU
INSIDE THE DOOR OF THE CLUB
WITH OFFICER MANZON.
- I WILL BE ROVING,
PLACING MYSELF
WHEREVER I BELIEVE
MOST EFFECTIVE.
- IF WE'RE GONNA
TAKE THEM OUTSIDE,
SHOULDN'T WE BE OUTSIDE?
- IN ORDER NOT TO STAND OUT
LIKE SORE THUMBS,
WE WILL CONTINUE WITH THE POSTS
WE'VE ALREADY ESTABLISHED.
THANK YOU,
DETECTIVES MORGAN AND QUINN.
THAT'LL BE ALL.
- MARIA...
LET ME MAKE MYSELF VERY CLEAR.
YOU'VE WASTED MORE THAN ENOUGH
TIME AND MONEY
ON THIS CASE ALREADY.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE A MASTER
MANIPULATOR OF THE PRESS,
BUT YOU HAVEN'T EVEN BEEN ABLE
TO DO THAT.
EVERY DAY I PICK UP THE PAPER,
READ ANOTHER STORY
ABOUT HOW WE'RE NOT
DOING OUR JOB.
GET IT RIGHT THIS TIME...
OR WE'RE GONNA HAVE
AN INTERESTING CONVERSATION
ABOUT YOUR FUTURE.
- [sighs]
WHERE ARE WE
WITH JORDAN CHASE?
- I'VE GOT QUINN ON IT.
WE'VE MADE NUMEROUS CALLS
TO HIS ORGANIZATION,
BUT WE HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO
REACH HIM PERSONALLY JUST YET.
HE COULD BE PLAYING
HARD TO GET.
[elevator bell rings]
IN THAT CASE,
WE'LL PAY HIS OFFICE A VISIT
TO SEE IF, UH--
- PROBABLY WON'T BE NECESSARY.
- JORDAN CHASE.
- UH, HI.
- HOLY SHIT.
THAT'S HIM.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
- YOU TOO.
- MR. CHASE?
OH, MR. CHASE.
- STAND BACK.
- I, UM--I, UH--
I TOOK ONE OF YOUR SEMINARS
AT THE BEACH CLUB
A WHILE BACK.
- SURE.
IN PALMETTO BAY.
- YOU REMEMBER?
- OF COURSE I DO.
YOU HAVE TO EXCUSE COLE HERE.
HE, UH--HE KEEPS
THE CRAZIES AWAY.
- WHY DON'T YOU LET ME GET
A PICTURE OF YOU TWO?
- OH, YEAH.
EXCELLENT. OKAY.
OKAY.
- ALL RIGHT.
SMILE.
[camera shutter clicks]
UH, ONE MORE.
GOT IT.
- JORDAN CHASE.
- DEXTER MORGAN.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
- WOW.
NICE WATCH.
- OH, UH, MY DAD
GAVE IT TO ME
WHEN I WAS A TEENAGER.
IT'S, UH, WATER-RESISTANT
TO 100 METERS.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHY
I WOULD EVER NEED THAT,
BUT IT SURE LOOKS NICE.
- IF THAT'S THE WATCH
THAT LUMEN HEARD,
I'LL MAKE SURE IT
ACCOMPANIES YOU
TO THE BOTTOM
OF THE ATLANTIC.
- MR. CHASE.
- YOU MUST BE THE PERSON
IN CHARGE AROUND HERE.
I WAS IN JACKSONVILLE,
GOT AN EARLY CALL
FROM COLE HERE,
MY HEAD OF SECURITY,
SAYING THAT ONE OF OUR TRUCKS
HAD BEEN STOLEN
OUT OF OUR LOT
AND THAT IT JUST MIGHT
BE THE ONE
WE'D ALL BEEN WATCHING
ON THE NEWS.
I FLEW BACK
AS SOON AS I COULD.
- I SEE.
- WE FOUND AN ARTICLE
OF CLOTHING IN THE VEHICLE.
- MY JACKET.
IT'S MY PERSONAL VEHICLE.
I ALWAYS LEAVE
MY THINGS INSIDE.
- AND THE KEYS?
- THE KEYS?
- YEAH, WE FOUND THE KEYS
IN THE IGNITION.
THERE ARE A LOT OF WAYS
TO STEAL A CAR.
MOST THIEVES DON'T HAVE
THE ACTUAL KEY.
- I LEAVE A SPARE SET OF KEYS
ON A HOOK INSIDE OUR OFFICE.
ALL MY GUYS KNOW WHERE
TO FIND THEM,
IN CASE THEY NEED THE TRUCK.
HONESTLY,
THEY'RE JUST SITTING THERE.
ANYONE COULD HAVE GRABBED THEM.
- AND YOU'RE HEAD OF SECURITY?
- [scoffs]
YEAH, COLE.
I MIGHT HAVE TO TIGHTEN THINGS
UP A BIT, HMM?
- [sighs]
- I WANT TO MAKE IT VERY CLEAR
THAT THE MIAMI POLICE DEPARTMENT
HAS MY FULL COOPERATION.
MY ORGANIZATION
IS COMPLETELY OPEN TO YOU.
THIS IS A HORRIBLE,
HORRIBLE TRAGEDY.
PLEASE, ANYTHING I CAN DO
TO HELP FACILITATE
ITS RESOLUTION.
- WELL, THANK YOU, MR. CHASE.
- FIRST, WE'RE GONNA NEED
FINGERPRINTS
AND HAIR SAMPLES
FROM ALL YOUR EMPLOYEES,
STARTING WITH COLE.
- ABSOLUTELY.
AND IF I COULD ASK ONE FAVOR?
I'D APPRECIATE IT IF MY NAME
AND ORGANIZATION
WASN'T RELEASED TO THE PRESS.
BEING CONNECTED TO THIS IN ANY
WAY WOULD BE A P.R. NIGHTMARE.
I'M SURE YOU UNDERSTAND.
- AS LONG AS WE HAVE
YOUR CONTINUED COOPERATION,
THAT SHOULDN'T BE A PROBLEM.
- SOCIOPATHS CAN'T FEEL
PSYCHIC PAIN,
BUT THEY CAN FEEL
PHYSICAL PAIN.
- OW.
- SORRY.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT COLE?
- "IT WASN'T ME.
SOMEONE STOLE MY VEHICLE."
THE OLDEST EXCUSE
IN THE BOOK.
- STILL, IT DOES HAPPEN.
AND MR. CHASE
IS VERY HIGH-PROFILE,
WELL RESPECTED.
IT'S HARD TO IMAGINE
SOMEONE LIKE HIM
OR HIS PEOPLE WOULD BE INVOLVED
IN SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
- I TOOK A FEW HAIRS
FROM THE HEADREST
OF THE TRUCK AS WELL.
IF SOMEONE ELSE WAS DRIVING,
HE'D HAVE LEFT
SOME EVIDENCE BEHIND.
- AND?
- WELL, COLE'S HAIR
MATCHES THE HAIR
ON THE JACKET
AND THE HEADREST.
- FINGERPRINTS?
- THEY'RE ALL COLE'S...
EVEN ON THE IGNITION KEY.
- I THINK HE'S JUST
BECOME THE FOCUS
OF OUR INVESTIGATION.
- AND JORDAN?
- HIS ALIBI HOLDS UP.
HE WAS IN JACKSONVILLE.
SO FOR NOW,
WE GOT OUR EYES ON COLE.
- LUMEN?
- DEXTER, YOU NEED
TO ANNOUNCE YOURSELF.
I DON'T KNOW WHO'S COMING IN.
- BUT IT'S OKAY TO HAVE PACKAGES
DELIVERED HERE?
[package thuds]
- I NEED THINGS.
YOU SAID NOT
TO LEAVE THE HOUSE.
- AND WHAT ARE YOU GONNA
DO WITH THAT?
- IT'S JUST A FLASHLIGHT.
- YOU HAVE A WAY
OF BENDING THE RULES.
- WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH THE CASE?
[keypad tones]
- DO YOU KNOW THIS MAN?
- OH, MY GOD.
THAT'S HIM.
THAT'S THE GUY
WHO FOLDED HIS JACKET.
HOW DID YOU FIND HIM?
- HE FOUND US.
HIS NAME'S COLE HARMON.
HE'S JORDAN CHASE'S
HEAD OF SECURITY.
[keypad tone]
WHAT ABOUT HIM?
- [sighs]
NO, I--
I MEAN, THAT GUY'S
CLEARLY A FREAK,
BUT I DON'T KNOW HIM.
- NO, NOT THE BALD GUY.
THE GUY BESIDE HIM--
JORDAN CHASE.
- OH.
NO, I DON'T KNOW HIM EITHER.
- YOU SURE?
- I TOLD YOU, I DIDN'T SEE
MOST OF THEIR FACES.
- [sighs]
- WHO IS HE?
- HE'S SOME SORT
OF MOTIVATIONAL SPEAKER.
- THIS GUY...
I DEFINITELY KNOW.
WHAT NEXT?
- WELL, THERE'S A PROBLEM.
THE HOMICIDE TEAM IS ON THIS.
THEY'LL PROBABLY ARREST HIM
WITHIN THE NEXT FEW DAYS,
AND ONCE THAT HAPPENS,
COLE WILL NEVER SEE
THE OUTSIDE
OF A PRISON CELL AGAIN.
- WHAT ABOUT THE OTHER GUYS?
- IN ORDER TO SAVE HIS OWN SKIN,
HE'LL PROBABLY TURN THEM IN.
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE THEY'RE ALL
IN THE HANDS OF THE POLICE.
BUT THIS IS FLORIDA.
WE EXECUTE HERE.
THESE MEN WILL BE BROUGHT
TO JUSTICE.
YOU CAN WALK AWAY
FROM ALL OF THIS NOW,
PUT IT BEHIND YOU.
YOU CAN GO ON WITH YOUR LIFE.
- NO.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I WANT.
- I PROMISE YOU THE POLICE
WILL TAKE CARE OF IT.
- NO, I DON'T WANT THE POLICE
TO TAKE CARE OF IT.
I--I WANT TO TAKE CARE OF IT.
- I KNOW HOW SHE FEELS.
IT'S NOT SO DIFFERENT
FROM ME.
HOW MUCH COFFEE
ARE YOU DRINKING?
- A LOT.
I HAVE TO STAY AWAKE.
WHAT IF THEY COME
FOR ME AT NIGHT?
- SHE'S STRESSED, ON EDGE--
THE WAY I FEEL
WHEN I'VE GONE TOO LONG
WITHOUT PUTTING SOMEONE
ON MY TABLE.
- YOU SAID YOU'D HELP ME.
- I DID.
I JUST DON'T KNOW
THAT HELPING YOU
KILL SOMEONE
IS ACTUALLY HELPING YOU.
- [sighs]
THIS IS ALL I THINK ABOUT.
DON'T BACK OUT NOW.
THIS IS IMPORTANT TO ME.
- [sighs]
TRUTH IS, I ACTUALLY WANT
TO HELP HER...
[sighs]
FOR SOME
VERY COMPLICATED REASONS.
IF WE WANT COLE
FOR OURSELVES,
I HAVE TO DERAIL
THE POLICE INVESTIGATION,
WHICH MEANS GIVING THEM
ANOTHER SUSPECT.
- WHO?
- THE MAN WHO ACTUALLY KILLED
ALL THOSE GIRLS--
BOYD FOWLER.
HERE, PUT THESE ON.
FIRST THING WE HAVE TO DO
IS REMOVE ANY EVIDENCE
THAT YOU WERE EVER HERE
AT BOYD'S HOUSE.
IF THE POLICE FIND
YOUR FINGERPRINTS OR...
ANYTHING THAT TIES YOU
TO THIS PLACE,
THEY'RE GONNA WANT TO KNOW
WHAT YOUR RELATIONSHIP
TO BOYD FOWLER IS...
HOW YOU GOT HERE...
HOW YOU GOT OUT.
- THAT'S WHERE YOU
FIRST FOUND ME.
- WE NEED TO GO UP.
YOU OKAY?
I'LL BE WITH YOU.
- [breathes sharply]
OH, GOD.
- YOU OKAY?
WE CAN LEAVE.
- NO.
HE KEPT ME TIED UP...
OVER THERE.
I DON'T KNOW
HOW LONG I WAS HERE...
MAYBE A COUPLE DAYS.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT HE BROUGHT ME
HERE TO KILL ME.
- I'M GUESSING
THAT WAS HIS JOB.
HE WAS THE FINISHER.
- THE LAST DAY,
I CHEWED ON THAT ROPE FOR HOURS.
I WAS FINALLY ABLE
TO SLIP IT OFF.
THAT'S WHEN I WENT DOWNSTAIRS,
AND I SAW YOU--
- DO WHAT I DID.
- [exhales sharply]
IS THAT IT?
- YEAH.
I JUST NEED SOMETHING
OF BOYD'S TO PLANT
IN THE TRUCK
FROM THE ACCIDENT.
HIS WALLET.
- HOW DID YOU KNOW
THAT WAS THERE?
- I PUT IT THERE.
- HOLD THE FUCKING PHONE,
EVERYONE!
I WAS GIVING COLE'S TRUCK
ANOTHER QUICK ONCE-OVER
AND I FOUND SOMETHING
THAT OUR BLIND-AS-FUCKING-BATS
LAB GEEKS MISSED.
- WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
- A WALLET.
HE PROBABLY HAD IT SITTING
ON THE CONSOLE,
AND THEN IT WENT FLYING
WHEN HE GOT HIT.
I FOUND IT UNDER THE SEAT.
- COLE'S WALLET?
- NO, THAT'S JUST IT.
IT'S NOT COLE'S.
- WHOSE IS IT?
- BOYD FOWLER'S.
- WHO THE FUCK
IS BOYD FOWLER?
[indistinct radio chatter]
- I'M GOING UPSTAIRS.
- CHECK IT OUT.
THERE ARE LOCKS OF HAIR
IN HERE
NUMBERED 1 THROUGH 12.
- 12?
JESUS.
WELL, I'LL RUN DNA
ON ALL THE HAIR SAMPLES
AND MATCH IT TO THE VICTIMS.
- THE GUY THAT DID THIS--
- DIED EXACTLY
WHERE YOU'RE STANDING.
- HEY.
IN HERE.
THE SAME EXACT BARREL
THE GIRLS WERE IN.
- JESUS.
WHAT'D HE DO WITH THESE?
- THE PRELIMINARY
MEDICAL EXAMINER'S REPORT
SAID ALL THE GIRLS
WERE ELECTROCUTED.
- WE'RE GONNA NEED FORENSICS
IN THE ATTIC.
I THINK HE KEPT
THE GIRLS UP THERE.
- IT LOOKS LIKE BOYD FOWLER
HAS BECOME OUR PRIMARY FOCUS.
DO YOU KNOW THIS MAN?
- NO.
- WELL, HE KNOWS YOU.
HE HAS ALL YOUR BOOKS
AND CDs IN HIS HOUSE.
- [stammers]
I'VE SOLD OVER A MILLION
COPIES OF MY BOOK,
ALMOST AS MANY CDs.
- I'M JUST TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT
HOW HE CAME TO BE DRIVING
YOUR TRUCK.
- [sighs]
WELL, I'M SORRY, BUT--
- I KNOW HIM...
BOYD FOWLER.
HE WAS ONE OF YOUR STALKERS.
- AND HOW COME
I'M JUST NOW HEARING THIS?
- NO REASON TO TELL YOU ABOUT
EVERY NUT THAT PASSES THROUGH.
HE NEVER SEEMED
LIKE A SERIOUS THREAT.
HE TOOK A FEW SEMINARS
A WHILE BACK
AND THEN STARTED SHOWING UP
AT OUR OFFICE
ASKING FOR MR. CHASE.
I HAD TO ESCORT HIM OFF
THE PREMISES A FEW TIMES.
HE WAS CLEARLY A BIT OFF,
BUT, UH, HE NEVER STRUCK ME
AS DANGEROUS.
- HE'S DANGEROUS.
- HE'D BEEN IN AND OUT
OF OUR OFFICES ENOUGH TIMES...
PROBABLY SAW
WHERE I PUT THE KEYS.
- WHEN'S THE LAST TIME
YOU HAD CONTACT WITH HIM?
- HAVEN'T SEEN HIM
FOR A WHILE...
COUPLE OF MONTHS MAYBE.
- ANY IDEA WHERE HE MIGHT BE?
- NO.
- WE HAVE A WARRANT
FOR HIS ARREST.
I SUGGEST THAT YOU BE
ESPECIALLY CAUTIOUS, MR. CHASE,
BECAUSE IF HE HAS
A THING FOR YOU,
YOU COULD BE IN DANGER.
- NOTED.
- NOW, IF YOU HAVE
ANY CONTACT WITH HIM,
PLEASE GET IN TOUCH
WITH US IMMEDIATELY.
THIS GUY IS VERY BAD NEWS.
- I WILL.
- THANK YOU FOR COMING IN.
I APPRECIATE IT.
- YOU FINALLY
DID SOMETHING RIGHT...
STEERING THE COPS
TOWARD BOYD--
VERY SMART.
- IT WASN'T ME.
- DADDY'S GOING
TO BOCA RATON TONIGHT,
'CAUSE THAT'S
WHERE COLE HARMON LIVES.
HE'S A BAD MAN.
I'M GONNA TRY TO FIND OUT
WHO THE REST
OF HIS BAD-MAN FRIENDS ARE.
YOU WANT THAT?
[knock on door]
[door opens]
- HI.
THERE'S MY ANGEL.
LET ME JUST SET
MY THINGS DOWN.
- WONDER HOW MUCH LONGER
I'M GONNA BE ABLE
TO TALK TO YOU LIKE THIS.
SOON YOU'RE GONNA START
TO UNDERSTAND ME.
- HARRISON CLEARLY LOVES
HIS SAINT BRIGID.
HE PUT IT
WITH HIS FAVORITE TOYS.
- I PUT THAT IN THE TOY BOX.
- SORRY?
- IT'S JUST A STATUE OF A LADY
WHO DIED A LONG TIME AGO.
SHE DOESN'T PROTECT ANYBODY
OR ANYTHING.
I SHOULD GET TO WORK.
HERE.
GO TO SONYA.
OH.
- IT'S JUST THIS CAN BE
A VERY DARK WORLD AT TIMES,
AND SINCE DEAR BRIGID
HAS ALWAYS BEEN A COMFORT TO ME,
I THOUGHT HARRISON
MIGHT FEEL THE SAME.
I HOPE FOR HIS SAKE,
YOU'D RECONSIDER.
- SURE.
BYE, BUDDY.
[door opens]
- SO, UH...
WHAT ARE YOU WEARING TONIGHT?
- TO THE BIG STAKEOUT?
UM, A DIAPER PROBABLY.
- [laughs]
- I'LL HAVE TO SIT IN THAT VAN
WITH BATISTA FOR HOURS.
WILL YOU PLEASE NOT WEAR
THAT AWFUL SHIRT
WITH THE PATTERNS ALL OVER IT?
IT REALLY MAKES ME DIZZY.
- NO, I, UH, ONLY WORE
THAT AS A JOKE.
[knock on door]
- OH.
- HEY, UH, I GOT TO GO.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER TONIGHT.
- OKAY.
[keypad tone]
- HEY.
- [chuckles] WELL, LOOK AT YOU,
PRETTY AS A PICTURE.
- [chuckles]
I ONLY GOT A FEW MINUTES,
SO, UH, WHAT DO YOU GOT FOR ME?
- I DON'T WORK
FOR FREE, QUINN.
- ALL RIGHT, WELL,
I JUST GAVE YOU 500 BUCKS.
- AND I TOLD YOU
ABOUT THE GIRL.
BUT IF YOU WANT TO FIND OUT
WHO SHE IS,
WHERE SHE'S FROM, AND WHAT SHE'S
DOING IN THAT DAMN HOUSE,
I MIGHT HAVE TO EMPLOY
SOME METHODS
JUST A LITTLE BIT UNORTHODOX.
AND FOR THAT,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO PAY.
- I DON'T KNOW.
- I KNOW YOU GOT THE CASH.
- YEAH, IT'S NOT THAT.
- [chuckles]
IT'S THE PUSSY.
NOW, LOOKY HERE, STUD,
IF YOU'RE BACKING OFF
THIS THING
'CAUSE YOU'RE PORKING
THAT GUY'S SISTER,
I'D SAY YOU'VE GOT
YOUR PRIORITIES AS A COP
ALL WRONG.
I'M A LITTLE EMBARRASSED
FOR YOU.
- I'LL GIVE YOU ANOTHER FIVE.
- [sighs]
THAT'LL WORK.
[overlapping chatter,
club music]
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO ANYTHING
WITH THIS, OKAY?
YOU CAN JUST TALK NORMALLY.
- WHAT DO I HAVE TO DO?
- WE'RE GONNA WALK YOU
THROUGH THE CLUB
SO THAT OUR TEAM CAN GET
A VISUAL ON YOU,
AND THEN YOU'RE JUST GONNA WAIT
BY THE DOOR.
- THE SECOND YOU SEE
THE FUENTES BROTHERS,
YOU WALK UP TO THEM,
AND YOU ENGAGE IN CONVERSATION
OUTSIDE OF THE CLUB
UNTIL WE MOVE IN AND TAKE 'EM.
- WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO SAY?
- TELL 'EM HOW HOT THEY LOOK.
YOU REALLY DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT ANYTHING.
WE'RE GONNA BE RIGHT THERE.
- I'M GONNA MAKE SURE
WE'RE ALL IN CONTACT.
THIS IS SERGEANT BATISTA.
IS EVERYBODY GETTING THIS?
- LOUD AND CLEAR.
- I CAN HEAR YOU.
- LOOKS LIKE WE'RE ALL
IN PLACE.
[club music]
* *
- OKAY.
- YOU'LL DO GREAT.
- THEY'RE ALREADY HERE.
- SAY AGAIN?
- I SAID THEY'RE ALREADY HERE,
SITTING AT THE V.I.P. TABLE.
- OKAY, HOW'D THAT HAPPEN?
I THOUGHT WE HAD
ALL THE DOORS COVERED.
- I DON'T KNOW.
I HEARD THERE'S A SECRET DOOR
FROM THE CLUB NEXT DOOR,
BUT I'VE NEVER SEEN IT.
- OKAY, THIS IS
A CHANGE OF PLANS.
YASMIN, GO SIT WITH THEM.
WE'RE GONNA SIT TIGHT
UNTIL THEY LEAVE.
ONCE THEY STEP OUTSIDE THE CLUB,
WE TAKE THEM.
LET'S MAKE SURE WE FIND
THAT SECRET DOOR
AND DEPLOY A TEAM THERE AS WELL.
EVERYONE GOT THAT?
- GOT IT.
- WE'VE BEEN HERE
FOR OVER AN HOUR.
- I KNOW.
- WELL, YOU SAID THERE'S
A SEMINAR IN NAPLES.
DON'T YOU THINK HE'S THERE?
- PROBABLY.
- SO WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
- [sighs]
THAT...
THE NEIGHBOR TO GO TO BED.
I'M GOING IN.
NO, YOU'RE STAYING HERE.
- WHAT?
NO.
- YES.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS.
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT'S INSIDE THERE.
I'M GONNA HAVE MY HANDS FULL
WITHOUT WATCHING OVER YOU.
- [closes car door]
FINE.
- WELL, YOU CAN...
BE THE LOOKOUT.
- IT'S SO GREAT WORKING
WITH YOU.
- IF YOU SEE ANYTHING,
CALL ME.
* *
- WE ARE STARTING
TO LOOK A LITTLE OBVIOUS.
I AM GONNA GO GET US
A CLUB SODA.
- ALL RIGHT, YEAH.
- [speaking Spanish]
- HE'S CALLING ME OVER.
- NO, KEEP MOVING.
IGNORE HIM.
- THIS IS LIEUTENANT LAGUERTA.
OFFICER MANZON, GO TO HIM,
MAKE NICE,
AND TRY TO GET HIM
TO STEP OUTSIDE THE CLUB.
- LIEUTENANT, NO.
THIS IS A PROBLEM.
THESE GUYS ARE DANGEROUS.
- STAND DOWN, MORGAN.
- SHE'S IN CHARGE.
NOTHING WE CAN DO.
- [speaking Spanish]
- NO.
[speaking Spanish]
- [speaking Spanish]
[gunshot]
- POLICE!
DROP THAT FUCKING GUN!
[gunshot]
- HOLY FUCKING SHIT!
[screaming]
MOVE! MOVE! MOVE!
[patrons screaming]
STOP RIGHT THERE.
DOWN ON THE GROUND.
POLICE!
DROP THE GUN!
- BACK AWAY!
- DROP THE GUN NOW!
- OH, YOU AGAIN.
YOU SHOULD WALK AWAY
BEFORE THIS ONE
GETS MORE THAN
JUST A LITTLE CUT.
- DROP THE GUN RIGHT NOW.
- [crying]
PLEASE!
[gunshot]
- YOU OKAY?
- YEAH.
YEAH.
- IT'S OKAY.
COME HERE.
- COLE AS A TEENAGER.
[grunts]
- WHO THE FUCK ARE YOU?
[house alarm sounds]
NO FUCKING WAY!
WHO ARE YOU, MOTHERFUCKER?
[grunts]
- [grunting]
- WE HAVE TO GO
BEFORE HE SEES OUR FACES.
- HOLY SHIT!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT JUST HAPPENED!
- WHAT MADE YOU COME INSIDE?
- I THOUGHT I SAW A SHADOW.
- AND THAT MADE YOU COME
CRASHING THROUGH A WINDOW?
- I KNOW. I KNOW.
I JUST HAD A FEELING.
IT WAS SOME SORT
OF LIZARD-BRAIN THING.
- SHE'S STARTING
TO SOUND LIKE ME.
THAT'S COLE.
- AND BOYD.
- AND DAN THE DENTIST.
- IT'S THEM FROM, LIKE,
15 YEARS AGO.
- DO YOU RECOGNIZE ANY
OF THE OTHERS?
- NO, JUST THOSE THREE.
- WHAT DOES THIS MEAN?
- I DON'T KNOW.
THEY'VE KNOWN EACH OTHER
SINCE THEY WERE KIDS.
OH, MY GOD, DEXTER.
THIS IS HUGE.
WE JUST HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
WHO THEY ARE.
- SO WHAT DO WE DO NEXT?
WHAT?
- YOU SAID "WE."
- PUT ON YOUR SEAT BELT.
[sighs]
- THIS IS A FUCKING DISASTER.
- CARLOS FUENTES
WAS SHOT AND KILLED.
OUR INFORMANT, YASMIN ARAGON,
WAS SHOT AND KILLED,
AS WELL
AS ANOTHER INNOCENT BYSTANDER.
- SON OF A BITCH.
- AT THIS POINT, WE DON'T KNOW
IF IT'S BY OUR GUNFIRE
OR THAT OF THE TWO BROTHERS.
ADDITIONALLY, THREE OTHER
BYSTANDERS WERE WOUNDED.
- I WANT A FULL REPORT
BY 8:00 A.M.
- I KNOW IT LOOKS BAD.
AND IT IS BAD...
BUT WE ARE GOING
TO GET THROUGH THIS.
I PROMISE YOU.
IN THE HEAT OF BATTLE...
ALL COPS MAKE OCCASIONAL
MISTAKES IN JUDGMENT.
- EXCUSE ME?
IF MISTAKES WERE MADE, THEY
MOST CERTAINLY WERE NOT MINE.
- HEY.
- HE WAS SO RELAXED
AND HAPPY,
I COULDN'T BEAR TO MOVE.
AND I HAVE TO ADMIT,
HE FEELS QUITE GOOD.
- HE'S ALWAYS SO HAPPY
IN HER ARMS.
PARTNERS COME TO US
IN VARIOUS WAYS,
BOUND TOGETHER
FOR MANY DIFFERENT REASONS.
BUT FOR ANY PARTNERSHIP
TO WORK,
YOU MUST NOT ONLY ACCEPT
THIS PERSON INTO YOUR LIFE,
BUT ACCEPT HER
FOR WHO SHE IS.
SAINT BRIGID...
CIRCLE US WITH YOUR LIGHT...
SO THAT NO DARKNESS
SHALL OVERCOME OUR WORLD.
HEY.
- HI.
HI.
HARRISON, THIS IS LUMEN.
- HI.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
HELLO.
[gasps and chuckles]
- SOMETIMES PARTNERS FIND US,
AND AS MUCH AS WE TRY
TO PUSH THEM AWAY,
THEY WORK THEIR WAY
INTO OUR LIVES REGARDLESS,
UNTIL WE FINALLY REALIZE
HOW MUCH WE NEED THEM.