- [speaking Spanish]
- PREVIOUSLY ON DEXTER...
[speaking Spanish]
- HE'S CALLING ME OVER.
- OFFICER MANZON,
GO TO HIM.
- LIEUTENANT, NO,
THIS IS A PROBLEM.
THESE GUYS ARE DANGEROUS.
- STAND DOWN, MORGAN.
- [shouts in Spanish]
- [screams]
- DROP THE GUN NOW!
[gunshot]
- OUR INFORMANT,
YASMIN ARAGON,
WAS SHOT AND KILLED.
- THIS IS
A FUCKING DISASTER.
- IF MISTAKES WERE MADE,
THEY MOST CERTAINLY
WERE NOT MINE.
- I JUST GAVE YOU 500 BUCKS.
- AND I TOLD YOU
ABOUT THE GIRL.
BUT IF YOU WANT
TO FIND OUT WHO SHE IS,
WHERE SHE'S FROM,
AND WHAT SHE'S DOING
IN THAT DAMN HOUSE,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO PAY.
- BOYD WASN'T THE ONLY ONE
WHO DID THIS TO ME.
THERE WERE OTHERS.
BESIDES THE ONES THAT
WE'VE ALREADY TAKEN CARE OF,
SUIT AND TIE.
HE'D TAKE OFF HIS JACKET
AND FOLD IT VERY CAREFULLY,
LIKE HE DIDN'T
WANT TO MESS IT UP.
- SOMEONE TRIED TO MOVE
THE GIRLS IN THE BARRELS.
- WHERE'S THE DRIVER?
- HE TOOK OFF.
- THAT MEANS
HE'S STILL MINE TO FIND.
- YOU'RE NEVER GONNA GUESS
WHO THIS TRUCK IS REGISTERED TO.
- JORDAN CHASE.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
- DO YOU KNOW THIS MAN?
- THAT'S THE GUY
WHO FOLDED HIS JACKET.
- HIS NAME'S COLE HARMON.
HE'S JORDAN CHASE'S
HEAD OF SECURITY.
THAT'S COLE.
- AND BOYD.
- AND DAN THE DENTIST.
- IT'S THEM
FROM, LIKE, 15 YEARS AGO.
- WHAT DOES THIS MEAN?
[quirky music]
* *
[slow, ominous music]
**
Jordan: WE ARE BORN PRIMAL.
[bear growling]
CONCEIVED WITH THE IMPULSE
TO FIGHT...
[eagle shrieks]
FOR WHAT WE DESIRE.
IT'S WRITTEN IN OUR GENES.
IT'S ENGRAVED IN OUR SOULS.
BUT WE'VE TRADED
THE WILDERNESS FOR PAVEMENT,
TREES FOR SKYSCRAPERS.
WE'VE LOST TOUCH
WITH OUR INSTINCTS,
WITH WHAT WE ARE.
WE HAVE FALLEN
FROM NATURE'S GRACE.
BUT WE SHALL BE DELIVERED!
[wild cheering]
IT'S TIME TO TAP
INTO YOUR PRIMAL SELVES
AND SEIZE THE POWER
OF INSTINCT.
WE'RE GONNA CAST OFF
THOSE SHACKLES
THAT BIND US
TO JOBS WE HATE,
PEOPLE WE DON'T LOVE,
LIVES THAT AREN'T
WORTH LIVING.
WE ARE GOING TO...
all: TAKE IT!
Dexter: I'VE NEVER BEEN
AROUND SO MANY PEOPLE
THAT MADE ME FEEL NORMAL.
- YEAH!
YEAH!
Dexter: REALLY NORMAL.
- THE POWER OF RISK!
crowd: TAKE IT!
- THE POWER OF DESIRE.
- THE POWER OF INSTINCT.
crowd: TAKE IT!
Dexter: INSTINCTS
ARE ALL I'VE EVER HAD.
COLE HARMON,
CHASE'S CHIEF OF SECURITY--
TORTURER, RAPIST, KILLER.
IT'S TIME TO TAP
INTO MY PRIMAL SELF.
- THE POWER OF LIFE!
crowd: TAKE IT!
- WE'RE GONNA TAKE IT!
- TAKE IT!
crowd: TAKE IT!
- ALL RIGHT.
[cheers and applause]
- LIEUTENANT LAGUERTA!
- LIEUTENANT,
MULTIPLE ROUNDS WERE FIRED
AT THE RECENT
CLUB MAYAN SHOOTOUT.
WAS MIAMI METRO RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE DEATHS
OF INNOCENT BYSTANDERS?
- I HAVE NOTHING TO SAY
AT THIS TIME.
EXCUSE ME.
- DO YOU AGREE
WITH THE MAYOR'S ASSESSMENT?
DID THIS OPERATION NEEDLESSLY
PUT PEOPLE AT RISK?
- EVERY UNDERCOVER OPERATION
IS HIGH RISK.
- IS THERE GOING TO BE
AN INDEPENDENT INVESTIGATION
OF THE SHOOTING?
- NO COMMENT.
- HAVE YOU PERSONALLY
RETAINED COUNSEL?
- COUNSEL?
- ISN'T IT TRUE
THE VICTIMS' FAMILIES
HAVE FILED A CIVIL LAWSUIT?
- LET ME THROUGH.
EXCUSE ME.
LET ME THROUGH.
- LIEUTENANT LAGUERTA
NEITHER CONFIRMING NOR DENYING
MIAMI METRO'S CULPABILITY
IN THE RECENT CLUB MAYAN
SHOOTOUT.
AS WE KNOW, TWO INNOCENT PEOPLE
ARE DEAD, SIX...
[mutes sound]
- DID BALLISTICS COME IN?
- IT'S GOOD NEWS.
BULLETS FROM THE VICTIMS' BODIES
BELONG TO THE FUENTES BROTHERS,
NOT US.
- THAT IS GOOD NEWS.
BUT THIS IS FAR FROM OVER.
I'M SURE YOU ALL HEARD
THE MAYOR'S STATEMENT.
- A PRIME EXAMPLE OF HOW SHIT
JUST ROLLS DOWNHILL.
- HE SHOULD HAVE
KEPT HIS MOUTH SHUT
UNTIL ALL
THE FACTS CAME OUT.
- HE WAS RIGHT.
THIS OPERATION WAS TOO RISKY.
AND NOW BECAUSE OF US,
TWO INNOCENT PEOPLE
ARE DEAD.
- NOT BY OUR BULLETS.
- SHOTS WOULD HAVE
NEVER BEEN FIRED
IF WE HADN'T BEEN SET UP
ON THAT CLUB.
THOSE ARE THE FACTS.
- ON THE UPSIDE,
CARLOS FUENTES IS DEAD,
- NONE OF US
SHOULD HAVE ANY ILLUSIONS.
THERE ARE GONNA BE
CONSEQUENCES.
- YEAH, I'VE SEEN
THAT LOOK ON HER FACE BEFORE.
SOMEONE'S ABOUT
TO GET BENT OVER AND FUCKED.
- IT'S GONNA BE ME,
ISN'T IT?
I SCREWED UP.
- NO, YOU DIDN'T.
YOU WERE FOLLOWING ORDERS.
LAGUERTA'S ORDERS,
JUST LIKE THE REST OF US.
THAT'S WHAT YOU PUT
IN YOUR REPORT, RIGHT?
YOU WERE FOLLOWING HER LEAD?
- I HAVEN'T WRITTEN IT YET.
I'M STILL SORTING
THROUGH THE EVENTS IN MY MIND.
- SORTING THROUGH WHAT
EXACTLY?
- WHAT I'M GONNA
SAY ABOUT THEM.
- HERE'S A CRAZY IDEA.
HOW ABOUT THE TRUTH?
- DEB, I'M ON IT.
[elevator bell rings]
- WHO'S THAT?
- IT'S YASMIN'S MOTHER.
- YOU ALL RIGHT?
- THREE PEOPLE ARE DEAD--
CARLOS FUENTES
AND TWO GIRLS.
NOBODY'S CRYING ABOUT CARLOS.
- FUENTES WAS A SCUMBAG.
- YEAH, HE'S A SCUMBAG
THAT I SHOT AND KILLED.
- AND?
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
DON'T TELL ME YOU FEEL BAD
ABOUT KILLING HIM.
- I DON'T.
THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
- YASMIN
DIDN'T FEEL ANY PAIN.
SHE DIED INSTANTLY.
- I'M READY.
- OKAY.
[sobbing]
- I HAVE SOME BAD NEWS
FOR EVERYONE.
- [sighs]
- YOU'RE ALL GOING TO DIE.
Dexter: SOME OF US
SOONER THAN OTHERS.
- SOME OF US SOONER
THAN OTHERS.
AND IF YOU'RE NOT IN TOUCH
WITH YOUR PRIMAL SELF,
YOU'RE ALREADY DEAD.
YOU MAY BE BREATHING
AND WALKING AROUND,
BUT YOU'RE AN EMPTY SHELL,
JUST ONE OF THE HERD,
COMPLETELY UNAWARE
OF WHAT YOU TRULY WANT.
AND WHEN WE COME BACK,
WE'RE GONNA START USING
YOUR INSTINCTS
TO DESIGN THE LIFE
THAT YOU DESERVE,
FUEL THE PASSION
TO MAKE IT REAL,
AND FIND THE POWER...
TO TAKE IT.
[cheers and applause]
female announcer: JORDAN CHASE'S
"TAKE IT NOW" EXPERIENCE
WILL RESUME AT 2:00 P.M.
IN THE MEANTIME, WE INVITE YOU
TO VISIT OUR VENDORS.
Dexter:
JORDAN PROMISES CHANGE,
BUT HE ALSO
ACCEPTS CREDIT CARDS.
[cell phone vibrating]
LUMEN?
- CAN YOU TALK?
OR ARE YOU ABOUT TO HAVE
A MAJOR LIFE REVELATION?
- NO, THAT CAME
AROUND 9:00 A.M.
WHEN I REALIZED
I REALLY WANTED A DOUGHNUT.
WHAT'D YOU FIND?
- I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO FIND OUT
HOW THESE GUYS
KNOW EACH OTHER.
THE PICTURE WAS TAKEN
WHEN THEY WERE TEENAGERS, BUT...
- DID YOU CHECK HIGH SCHOOLS?
- COLE WENT TO WESTLAND PREP
IN HIALEAH,
AND DAN THE DENTIST
WENT TO
ST. JOSEPH'S ACADEMY
IN CORAL GABLES.
BOYD...
THERE'S NOTHING ON BOYD.
- YEAH,
HE PROBABLY NEVER SAW
THE INSIDE OF
TOO MANY CLASSROOMS.
- I WAS ABLE TO FIND OUT
SOMETHING ELSE ABOUT COLE.
- WHAT?
- HE WAS IN THE MARINES.
HE GOT BOUNCED
ON DISHONORABLE DISCHARGE.
HE BEAT UP
A SUPERIOR OFFICER
AND PUT HIM
IN THE HOSPITAL.
THIS IS
A DANGEROUS GUY, DEXTER.
DO YOU REMEMBER THE MARKS
I HAD ON MY BACK?
THAT WAS COLE.
SO BE CAREFUL.
- YOU GETTING ANY REST?
- I FALL INTO A DEEP SLEEP
FROM 1:00 TO 1:15 EVERY MORNING.
WHEN THIS IS OVER,
I EXPECT TO SLEEP FOR A YEAR.
- I'LL TALK TO YOU LATER.
- MR. MORGAN.
COLE HARMON.
I'M SURE YOU REMEMBER ME
FROM OUR VISIT TO THE STATION.
MR. CHASE SPOTTED YOU
FROM THE STAGE.
HE'S VERY INTERESTED
IN SPEAKING WITH YOU.
HE WAS WONDERING
IF YOU'D JOIN HIM
IN HIS SUITE
FOR A FEW MINUTES.
- UH...OKAY.
WHEN?
- HOW ABOUT RIGHT NOW?
ALL THE WAY TO THE END.
TURN RIGHT.
[lock beeps]
- I'M DISGUSTED,
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH.
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN LISTENING
TO A WORD I'VE SAID.
[door closes]
CALL ME BACK WHEN YOU STOP
BEING A PIECE OF FURNITURE.
[Bluetooth beeps]
- SORRY.
NEW CLIENT.
GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN,
MR. MORGAN,
ESPECIALLY UNDER
BETTER CIRCUMSTANCES.
- CALL ME DEXTER.
- JORDAN.
CAN I OFFER YOU A DRINK?
- UH, NO, THANKS.
I'M GOOD.
- THINK I KNOW WHY YOU'RE HERE.
- YOU DO?
- YOU'RE SEARCHING FOR A WAY
TO COPE WITH YOUR LOSS.
I KNOW YOUR HISTORY,
DEXTER.
I THOUGHT I RECOGNIZED YOU
WHEN WE MET AT THE STATION,
BUT IT HIT ME LATER ON.
YOU WIFE WAS MURDERED.
- YES.
- THEY ANY CLOSER
TO CATCHING TRINITY?
- NOT THAT I'M AWARE OF.
- I FOLLOWED THAT CASE
VERY CLOSELY.
TRINITY--A RELIGIOUS MAN,
FAMILY, GOOD LIFE.
YET HE WAS WORKING
THROUGH SUCH RAGE,
HARBORING
SO MANY SECRETS.
I HAVE TO BE HONEST.
HE FASCINATED ME
ON A DEEP LEVEL.
- WHAT ELSE DO JORDAN
AND I HAVE IN COMMON?
- I CERTAINLY DON'T MEAN
TO IMPLY ANY SYMPATHY FOR HIM.
HE'S A MONSTER,
NO QUESTION.
I CAN'T IMAGINE
YOUR FRUSTRATION,
KNOWING HE'S OUT THERE,
UNPUNISHED.
- IT HASN'T BEEN EASY.
- NO DOUBT.
- AND NOW YOU'RE
A SINGLE FATHER,
WHICH HAS ITS OWN SET
OF CHALLENGES.
- WHY DID YOU
WANT TO SEE ME?
- I'VE DEVELOPED A THEORY
ON HOW THE PRIMAL SELF
DEALS WITH TRAGEDY.
[exhales]
I HAVE TO PREPARE
FOR THE NEXT SESSION,
BUT I AM VERY INTERESTED
IN WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU.
I WOULD LIKE TO DISCUSS
YOUR SITUATION IN DEPTH
AT ANOTHER TIME
IF YOU'RE OPEN TO THAT.
- OKAY.
BY THE WAY, HAVE YOU MADE
ANY PROGRESS ON BOYD FOWLER?
- I'M NOT REALLY AWARE
OF ALL THE DETAILS.
YOU SHOULD PROBABLY SPEAK TO
ONE OF THE DETECTIVES.
- OF COURSE.
I LOOK FORWARD
TO OUR NEXT TALK.
THERE'S A LITTLE SOMETHING
IN THERE FOR HARRISON.
- THANKS.
- YOU WANTED TO SEE ME?
- CLOSE THE DOOR.
- [sighs]
YOU KNOW THERE'S A LOT OF HEAT
COMING DOWN ON US,
AND THE PUBLIC'S
DEMANDING BLOOD, OUR BLOOD.
MATTHEWS WANTS
SOMEONE'S HEAD.
- SOUNDS LIKE
SANTA MUERTE'S CATCHING ON.
- I'M PUTTING CIRA MANZON
ON DISCIPLINARY LEAVE.
- WHAT?
- I NEED TO PUT
A FACE ON IT.
- WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOUR FACE?
- DETECTIVE--
- YOU CAN'T PIN THIS
ON HER.
- HER ACTIONS PRECIPITATED
THE SHOOTING.
- SHE WASN'T EVEN
SUPPOSED TO BE THERE.
I TRIED TO TAKE HER OFF,
AND YOU WOULDN'T LET ME.
- THAT'S YOUR IMPRESSION.
- NO, THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
LOOK, I WAS
THE DETECTIVE IN CHARGE,
SO IF YOU WANT TO FUCK
SOMEBODY OVER,
HERE'S YOUR SCAPEGOAT.
- I KNOW YOUR INSTINCT
IS TO TAKE THE FALL
FOR YOUR TEAM.
- YOU WERE ON MY TEAM.
IN FACT, YOU FUCKIN'
TOOK OVER MY TEAM,
AND I HAD YOUR BACK,
'CAUSE YOUR TEAM,
MY TEAM, WHATEVER,
IT'S ALL THE FUCKIN' SAME.
- CIRA'S JUST STARTING OUT.
HER CAREER WILL TAKE
THE SMALLEST HIT.
SHE'LL RECOVER QUICKLY.
- IF SOMETHING LIKE THAT
HAD HAPPENED TO ME BACK THEN,
I NEVER WOULD HAVE
MADE DETECTIVE.
WE WERE ALL THERE TOGETHER.
SO WHY CAN'T
WE JUST HOLD TIGHT
AND WEATHER
THE FUCKIN' STORM TOGETHER?
FUCKIN' THINK ABOUT IT.
[door opens and closes]
[cell phone rings]
- DOES YOUR PRINTER
EVER WORK?
- LU?
- OWEN.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- UM...
UM...
- I BET YOU'RE TAN.
THE SUN FEELS CLOSER HERE,
EVEN THOUGH I KNOW IT ACTUALLY
PHYSICALLY IS NOT,
IT FEELS LIKE
IT'S RIGHT THERE.
- YOU'RE IN MIAMI?
- I GOT A SUNBURN
JUST RENTING THE CAR.
I CAME TO SEE YOU.
- YOU DID?
- LU, I'VE RESPECTED
YOUR WISHES.
SINCE THE DAY
OF THE WEDDING,
I HAVEN'T CALLED,
I HAVEN'T EMAILED,
I HAVEN'T EVEN TEXTED.
IT'S LIKE MY LIFE
STOPPED THAT DAY
WHEN YOU LEFT,
AND I NEED TO GET UNSTUCK.
I FEEL THE WAY TO DO THAT
IS TO SEE YOU, FACE-TO-FACE,
WITHOUT 75 OF OUR CLOSEST
FRIENDS AND FAMILY
STARING AT US.
PLEASE, WILL YOU SEE ME?
- I...
[clears throat]
I CAN'T TONIGHT.
- TOMORROW.
[car engine rumbling]
[engine stops,
door opens]
LU?
I'M STAYING AT
THE BLUE PELICAN MOTEL.
THERE'S A CAFE
ACROSS THE STREET.
MEET ME THERE TOMORROW
AT NOON, OKAY?
- OKAY, NOON.
[phone beeps]
- HEY.
- I GOT YOU SOME SUPPER.
HOT AND SOUR SOUP,
FRIED RICE WITH TOFU.
THAT'S WHAT YOU LIKE,
RIGHT?
- YEAH, IT'S FINE.
- NO, I'M NOT STAYING.
- OH, RIGHT.
HARRISON.
- YOU'RE TIRED.
- I SPENT THE ENTIRE DAY
STARING AT THAT LAPTOP,
AND I GOT EXACTLY NOWHERE.
- WELL, THE GOOD NEWS IS
YOU WON'T BE
ON THAT COMPUTER TOMORROW.
I HAVE SOMETHING
I NEED YOU TO DO.
- WHAT?
- SHOPPING.
- WHAT KIND OF SHOPPING?
- SUPPLIES.
WE HAVE TO MAKE A ROOM
WHERE COLE
WILL BE DISPATCHED.
IT HAS TO BE COVERED
IN PLASTIC.
SO DOES COLE.
- TO CATCH THE BLOOD.
- I MADE A LIST.
DUCT TAPE, 30 YARDS
OF CLEAR POLYETHYLENE SHEETING.
- AND GARBAGE BAGS,
THREE MIL, BLACK.
- WHEN ARE YOU
GONNA DO IT?
- TOMORROW.
I BOOKED A ROOM
RIGHT NEXT TO COLE'S.
- YOU'RE GONNA DO IT
IN THE HOTEL?
- NO CHOICE.
JORDAN'S NEXT GIG
IS IN SARASOTA.
HE AND COLE WILL BE
HITTING THE ROAD
RIGHT AFTER
THE SEMINAR ENDS.
- SO...
TOMORROW NIGHT'S
THE NIGHT.
- THERE'S A PARKING LOT
RIGHT ON THE CORNER
OF FOURTH AND BAY.
MEET ME THERE
TOMORROW AT NOON,
AND I'LL PICK UP
THE SUPPLIES.
- 1:00 WOULD BE BETTER,
JUST SO I HAVE
ENOUGH TIME TO SHOP.
- SURE.
WHAT?
- A FEW MONTHS AGO, I WAS
SHOPPING FOR A WEDDING DRESS,
AND NOW I'M SHOPPING FOR...
30 YARDS
OF POLYETHYLENE SHEETING.
IT'S CRAZY, ISN'T IT,
HOW QUICKLY YOU CAN GET USED TO
THE SUPREMELY WEIRD?
- TELL ME ABOUT IT.
- THANKS FOR COVERING.
- NO PROBLEM.
SONYA JUST LEFT.
UGH. JORDAN CHASE.
I KNOW YOU'RE HURTING,
SO I'LL RESERVE JUDGMENT,
BUT I GOTTA DRAW
THE LINE SOMEWHERE.
- IT WAS FREE.
IT CAN'T HURT, CAN IT?
MAYBE I'LL COME AWAY
WITH SOMETHING.
- YEAH, A REALLY UGLY ONESIE.
I DON'T KNOW.
IF IT'S WORKING, WHO AM I
TO POOP ON YOUR PARADE?
- AND YOUR DAY?
- I'VE GOT SIX MANDATORY
SESSIONS WITH A SHRINK
COMING AT ME
BECAUSE OF CARLOS FUENTES.
FEELS LIKE A BIG, FAT
FUCKING WASTE OF TIME TOO.
I MEAN, I'D KILL THAT FUCKTARD
ALL OVER AGAIN.
I'D EMPTY
A FUCKING MAGAZINE IN HIM.
OKAY.
MAYBE THAT'S SOMETHING
WORTH TALKING ABOUT.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT
IF I LANDED A BULLET
THAT IT WOULD BOTHER ME,
THAT IT WOULD...
IT WOULD BE A BURDEN
TO TAKE ANOTHER LIFE.
THEY DON'T ISSUE GUNS
TO LAB GEEKS,
SO YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
- I CAN IMAGINE.
- I DON'T FEEL BAD.
ME, OF ALL PEOPLE.
I DON'T FEEL ANYTHING.
MAYBE I'VE JUST RUN OUT.
- DAD ONCE TOLD ME THAT...
SOME PEOPLE
DESERVE TO DIE.
- YOU BELIEVE THAT?
YOU BELIEVE SOME PEOPLE
DESERVE TO DIE?
- SOME PEOPLE DON'T
DESERVE TO LIVE.
- TRINITY SHOULD BE DEAD.
NOT RITA, NOT LUNDY.
MAYBE THE WORLD
IS BETTER OFF
WITHOUT CARLOS FUENTES.
- I'D PRETTY MUCH
GIVEN UP HOPE.
I FIGURED I WAS DESTINED
TO GO THROUGH LIFE ALONE,
AND THEN I STARTED LISTENING
TO ONE OF YOUR CDs.
- THE PRIMAL SELF?
- I STARTED LISTENING
IN THE CAR ON THE WAY TO WORK.
THREE WEEKS LATER,
I MET MY SOUL MATE,
AND NOW WE HAVE
A BABY ON THE WAY!
[cheers and applause]
- COME ON UP HERE.
- COME ON!
COME ON, HONEY!
Dexter: COLE WILL BE
AT HIS POST
FOR THE REST
OF THE SESSION.
THAT GIVES ME AN HOUR.
[lock beeps]
[aerosol hissing]
I'LL HAVE TO DO THIS
IN THE DARK.
14 STEPS TO THE PILLOW,
GIVE HIM THE NEEDLE,
AND DRAG HIM TO MY ROOM.
60 SECONDS TOPS.
JORDAN'S ABOUT TO LOSE
HIS NUMBER ONE FAN.
- OH.
- SORRY.
- NO, NO, IT'S ME.
REALLY.
- YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
- I DON'T, REALLY.
- YOU DO.
YOU ALWAYS DO.
MIAMI SUITS YOU.
- [scoffs]
- YOU MUST LOVE
ALL THESE ART DECO BUILDINGS.
- CAN'T GET ENOUGH OF 'EM.
- STEPH HAD HER BABY.
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
SHE WAS DUE LAST MONTH.
- YES. MEET MAVIS.
- LOOK AT HER.
MAVIS?
- MARK'S GRANDMOTHER.
THE NAME CAME DOWN
TO MAVIS OR MADISON.
- MADISON.
YOUR NIECE COULD
HAVE BEEN NAMED
AFTER THE CITY WHERE YOU AND I
DID OUR SUNDAY BEER RUNS.
- COOLER HEADS PREVAILED--
MINE.
- HOW IS STEPH DOING?
- SHE'S TIRED,
GLAD TO NOT BE PREGNANT
ANYMORE,
CRIES AT COMMERCIALS...
AND IS
TRANSCENDENTLY HAPPY.
YOUR PARENTS MISS YOU.
THEY'D LIKE TO KNOW
THAT YOU'RE SAFE.
- YOU CAN TELL THEM.
- WELL, I'M THINKING
OF NOT GOING BACK TOO.
- WHAT?
- YOU WERE RIGHT.
WE WERE TRAPPED IN OUR JOBS,
TRAPPED IN THAT CITY.
WE'D HAVE BEEN TRAPPED
IN A LIFE WE DIDN'T WANT.
IT'S TIME
FOR THAT TO CHANGE.
- OWEN?
- LU...
I BOUGHT THESE
ROUND THE WORLD TICKETS.
BROKE THE BANK.
WE CAN LITERALLY HOP ON
AND HOP OFF IN ANY CITY.
I LOVE YOU.
NO MATTER WHAT YOU DO,
WHOEVER YOU ARE,
I WANT TO TAKE
THIS JOURNEY WITH YOU.
HAVE YOU MET SOMEONE?
- I'VE MET
A LOT OF PEOPLE HERE,
BUT NOT
LIKE YOU'RE THINKING.
I CAN'T JUST LEAVE.
- ME SHOWING UP LIKE THIS
IS SUDDEN, I KNOW.
WE HAD FIVE YEARS.
TAKE A NIGHT
TO THINK IT OVER.
I'M GOING EITHER WAY,
BUT I'D RATHER GO WITH YOU.
MEET ME HERE
TOMORROW NIGHT
AND TELL ME
YOUR DECISION.
- GOD FUCKING DAMN IT.
- WHAT IS IT?
- UN-FUCKING-BELIEVABLE.
- LIEUTENANT,
WILL THERE BE ANY OTHER--
- I DON'T KNOW
WHO YOUR SOURCES ARE,
BUT I CAN CONFIRM
THAT DETECTIVE MORGAN
WAS IN CHARGE
OF THE OPERATION.
- HOLY SHIT.
- SHE'S BLAMING
EVERYTHING ON ME.
- IS IT TRUE
THAT DETECTIVE MORGAN
HAS BEEN PLACED
ON DISCIPLINARY LEAVE?
- AS OF TODAY,
SHE'S BEING PLACED
ON IMMEDIATE SUSPENSION
WITH PAY,
PENDING THE RESULTS OF--
- WHOA! NOT THE PLASMA.
- EXCUSE ME.
- I THOUGHT WE WERE
ACTUALLY FRIENDS.
- DEB, WAIT.
- I CAN'T DO IT.
I CAN'T LET HER THROW ME
UNDER THE BUS
AND DRIVE OVER ME,
THEN BACK UP A FEW FUCKIN' TIMES
AND DRIVE OFF.
[engine starts]
[crash]
- FUCK! SHIT! FUCK!
DIDN'T YOU
SEE ME DRIVING UP?
- DIDN'T YOU SEE ME
BACKING OUT?
- YOU KNOW,
THERE'S A REASON
WHY CARS
HAVE REARVIEW MIRRORS, LADY!
I MEAN, SHIT,
LOOK AT THAT.
THIS HERE'S FIBERGLASS.
CAN'T POUND THAT OUT.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO PULL
THAT WHOLE QUARTER PANEL OFF.
- HOW DO I KNOW
IT WASN'T ALREADY THERE?
- YOU JUST HIT MY CAR.
- I WAS DISTRACTED.
JUST LET ME GIVE YOU SOME CASH.
- NO CASH!
I DON'T WANT CASH!
WE'LL DO THIS
ON THE UP-AND-UP,
'CAUSE THAT'S THE KIND
OF GUY I AM.
WE JUST LET THE INSURANCE DUDES
HASH THIS OUT.
YOU DO HAVE INSURANCE,
DON'T YOU?
- YEAH.
- WELL, HALLE-FUCKIN'-LUJAH.
NOW, LET'S JUST, UH,
TRADE SOME INFO HERE
AND GET THIS SORTED OUT.
LOOK, NOW, WE CAN EITHER
DO THIS THE RIGHT WAY,
OR I CAN CALL UP THE PO-LICE,
LET MIAMI'S FINEST
HANDLE IT.
IT'S YOUR CALL.
- NO.
NO, NO, NO. I...
female announcer: THE JORDAN
CHASE EXPERIENCE SEMINAR
WILL RESUME TOMORROW
AT 8:00 A.M. SHARP.
VENDORS ARE OPEN TONIGHT
TILL 7:00 P.M.
- HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
Dexter: I GUESS WORKING
FOR JORDAN HAS ITS BENEFITS.
[cell phone rings]
[beeps]
HELLO?
- I'M HERE.
- I'M ON MY WAY.
- NO, I MEAN,
I'M HERE IN THE LOBBY.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- I GOT
INTO A CAR ACCIDENT.
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- YEAH, YEAH.
IT WAS MY FAULT.
ACTUALLY, NO,
IT WAS OWEN'S FAULT.
- OWEN WHO?
- MY EX-FIANCE.
HE'S IN MIAMI.
- WHY?
- HE CAME TO SEE ME.
DON'T WORRY, I DIDN'T TELL
HIM ANYTHING ABOUT ANYTHING.
HE ASKED ME
TO GO AWAY WITH HIM.
JUST UP
AND LEAVE ALL THIS BEHIND.
[scoffs]
AS IF I COULD.
- YOU COULD, YOU KNOW.
- DO YOU WANT ME TO GO?
- IF YOU WANT TO...
GO.
- THIS IS THE ONLY PART
OF MY LIFE
THAT MAKES SENSE
ANYMORE.
- WHAT ABOUT OWEN?
- HE'S LEAVING.
- WHEN?
- TOMORROW.
- STAY THE NIGHT.
THE SEMINAR'S
OUT FOR THE DAY,
AND COLE COULD BE ANYWHERE.
HE COULD SEE YOU.
IT'S TOO RISKY TO HAVE YOU
WALK THROUGH THE LOBBY AGAIN.
- IF I STAY,
DOES THAT MEAN YOU'RE
NOT GONNA KILL COLE TONIGHT?
- NO, IT'S STILL HAPPENING.
WE'RE GONNA PREPARE
THE ROOM TOGETHER.
[lock clicks]
Dexter: THIS IS ALL MUCH EASIER
WITH A PARTNER.
BUT A PARTNER IN WHAT?
[door slams]
- WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
- I WAS PLANNING TO.
I HAVE NO IDEA HOW THE PRESS
GOT HOLD OF IT.
- MAYBE IT WAS BECAUSE
YOU FUCKING LEAKED IT.
- YOU'LL BE A DESK JOCKEY
FOR A FEW WEEKS,
THEN YOUR UNION REP
WILL HAVE YOU REINSTATED.
THIS TIME NEXT YEAR,
ALL WILL HAVE BLOWN OVER.
- IT'S JUST YOUR WORD
AGAINST MINE
AND EVERYBODY ELSE
THAT WAS THERE.
- SOME PEOPLE DON'T AGREE
WITH YOUR VERSION
OF THE EVENTS.
- WHO'D YOU GET
TO LIE FOR YOU?
BATISTA?
BATISTA'S GONNA BACK
YOUR FUCKIN' STORY?
DO I HAVE TO GO
TO MATTHEWS WITH THIS?
- YOU WATCH YOURSELF,
DETECTIVE.
WE WOULDN'T WANT YOUR
REINSTATEMENT TO BE DELAYED.
- GOD.
I WAS FUCKING HAPPY
FOR YOU WHEN YOU GOT MARRIED.
I ACTUALLY THOUGHT THAT YOU
BEING WITH BATISTA
MIGHT MAKE YOU
A NICER PERSON.
I NEVER EXPECTED YOU
TO FUCKIN' EAT HIM ALIVE.
[plastic rustling]
- COLE'S OTHER VICTIMS.
WHY DID YOU PUT
THEIR PICTURES UP?
- COLE NEEDS TO SEE
WHAT HE'S DONE.
- WHAT DO YOU GET
OUT OF ALL THIS?
- I LIKE KNOWING THAT THE MEN
WHO DID THIS TO YOU
WON'T DO IT TO ANYONE ELSE.
- THIS ISN'T ABOUT ME.
- YOU'RE STANDING HERE.
- LOOK AT ALL THIS.
IF YOU DIDN'T KNOW ME,
YOU'D STILL BE IN THIS ROOM.
BOYD WASN'T YOUR FIRST.
YOU'VE BEEN DOING THIS
A LONG TIME.
[door opens]
- IT'S COLE.
WE'LL WAIT FOR HIM
TO GO TO SLEEP,
THEN YOU TAKE OFF
AND I GRAB HIM.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- M-99.
ANIMAL TRANQUILIZER.
GIVES ME A FEW HOURS
TO WRAP HIS BODY IN PLASTIC
AND SECURE HIM
TO THIS DESK.
- YOU'RE GONNA KILL HIM
WHILE HE'S STILL OUT?
- NO, I'M GONNA WAKE HIM UP,
SEE IF HE'LL GIVE UP
THE OTHER TWO NAMES
OF THE MEN
IN THE PICTURES.
MY KNIFE CAN BE
VERY PERSUASIVE.
[woman screams]
STAY HERE.
[screaming]
[screaming,
bed thumping]
- OWW!
TIE MY OTHER ARM!
DO IT NOW!
UNH! YES!
OHH! OHH!
OHH!
YES!
OH, GOD! OH!
[Lumen whimpering]
[woman screams]
- [whimpering]
[softly crying]
NO.
NO!
[woman screaming]
[Lumen's screams fade in]
NO! [screams]
NO MORE! PLEASE!
NO! NO!
NO! LET ME GO!
NO! LET ME OUT OF HERE!
[screams fade]
[Lumen breathing]
WHAT HAPPENED?
- YOU FELL ASLEEP.
- WHAT ABOUT COLE?
- HE'S BACK
AT THE SEMINAR BY NOW.
THE SCREAMER
SPENT THE NIGHT.
- SO YOU'RE
NOT GONNA KILL HIM?
- NO, I AM.
I'VE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT IT ALL NIGHT.
COLE MAKES HIS SECURITY ROUNDS
AT EVERY SESSION.
- SO...
- I'LL WAIT FOR HIM
BY THE SERVICE ELEVATOR
AND M-99 HIM THERE.
I WOULD HAVE RATHER
GRABBED HIM AT NIGHT,
BUT I CAN MAKE THIS WORK.
- AND WHAT ABOUT ME?
- YOU'LL WAIT
UNTIL THE SESSION STARTS.
EVERYONE WILL BE
IN THE SEMINAR.
YOU WON'T BE SPOTTED
WHEN YOU LEAVE.
JUST STEER CLEAR
OF THE SERVICE ELEVATOR.
- OKAY.
[exhales]
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
- WHAT?
- I ACTUALLY SLEPT.
- HEY.
DO YOU WANT TO GET UP?
- NO.
- DO YOU WANT TO GO
BACK TO SLEEP?
- NO.
- DO YOU WANT TO JUST--
NO, I JUST--I DON'T
WANT TO DO ANYTHING.
I JUST WANT TO LIE HERE.
IT'S SUNDAY.
I'M ALLOWED.
- LAGUERTA'S AN EVIL BITCH.
- NO, SHE'S NOT.
MAYBE SHE IS.
- THE BEST WAY
TO GET BACK AT HER
IS TO DO EXACTLY
WHAT SHE SAYS.
GO ON LEAVE,
TALK TO YOUR UNION REP,
GET REINSTATED,
THEN COME BACK AND KICK
AS MUCH ASS
AS YOU POSSIBLY CAN.
[doorbell rings]
NO ONE,
NOT EVEN LAGUERTA,
CAN DENY THAT YOU'RE
A GREAT DETECTIVE.
AT THE END OF THE DAY,
YOU'LL BE
THE ONE LEFT STANDING.
- AT THEN END OF THE DAY?
- YEAH, YOU KNOW,
WHEN ALL IS SAID AND DONE.
- SOUNDS LIKE
ONE VERY LONG DAY.
- HEY.
[sniffs]
I SMELL COFFEE.
- NOW'S NOT A GOOD TIME.
- WELL, IT IS FOR ME.
HEY, DEBRA MORGAN.
- LIDDY, RIGHT?
- GOOD MEMORY.
I LIKE THIS ONE.
- "THIS ONE"?
- YOU AND I GOT
SOMETHING IN COMMON.
WE'VE BOTH BEEN FUCKED OVER
BY LAGUERTA.
- WELL,
MAYBE WE SHOULD MAKE
MATCHING T-SHIRTS
OR SOMETHING.
- [laughs]
- OKAY.
WELL, THIS ONE'S GOING
FOR A FUCKIN'
BREAKFAST BURRITO.
I'LL SEE YOU TWO LATER.
- CALL BEFORE YOU COME OVER.
IT'S A COMMON COURTESY.
- DON'T YOU WANT TO KNOW
ABOUT THIS GIRL
SHACKED UP
WITH DEXTER MORGAN?
I JUST STAGED A LITTLE
MEET AND GREET WITH HER.
OLD P.I. MOVE.
- SO YOU MET HER.
- NAME, LUMEN PIERCE.
LUMEN--
STUPID FUCKIN' NAME.
FROM MINNEAPOLIS,
MINNESOTA.
SUPPOSED TO BE MARRIED
THREE MONTHS AGO,
PICTURE IN THE PAPER
AND EVERYTHING.
JUST TAKES OFF.
SHOWS UP HERE IN MIAMI
ONE WEEK BEFORE
YOUR BOY'S WIFE,
RITA MORGAN, IS MURDERED.
NOW, WHAT
YOU THINK OF THAT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
IS THAT ALL YOU GOT?
- IT'S A HELL OF LOT MORE
THAN I HAD YESTERDAY.
- WELL, STAY ON IT.
- I'D LOVE TO,
BUT I AM RUNNING OUT OF LOOT.
- I JUST PAID YOU
LAST WEEK.
- AND I JUST
FUCKED UP MY CAR
GETTING THIS INFO
FOR YOU, QUINN.
NOW, THIS BOY IS DIRTY.
WHAT YOU
GONNA DO ABOUT IT?
- I'M NOT GIVING YOU
ANY MORE.
- YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT YOU AND ME
HAD AN UNDERSTANDING.
I MEAN, IT'D BE A SHAME
IF THE SKIRT YOU'RE BONIN'
FINDS OUT ABOUT ALL THIS.
- AND HOW
WOULD THAT HAPPEN?
- I DON'T KNOW.
THINGS GO WRONG
EVERY DAY.
- FUCKIN' MOTHERFUCKER!
- [laughs]
YOU TWO ARE STARTIN'
TO SOUND MORE ALIKE EVERY DAY.
MUST BE LOVE.
- TRAGEDY.
MANY OF US HERE
HAVE EXPERIENCED IT
IN ONE FORM OR ANOTHER.
THE KIND THAT LEAVES
YOU WONDERING
IF THERE'S A REASON
TO GO ON LIVING.
FOR THE LAST TWO DAYS,
YOU'VE HEARD ME TALKING ABOUT
GETTING IN TOUCH
WITH YOUR PRIMAL SELF.
BUT HOW DOES THE PRIMAL SELF
DEAL WITH LOSS?
Dexter:
COLE'S STARTING HIS ROUNDS.
HE'LL REACH THE SERVICE ELEVATOR
IN FIVE MINUTES.
IN THREE MINUTES, SO WILL I.
- THERE'S SOMEONE
IN THIS ROOM
WHO IS DEALING
WITH THAT VERY QUESTION.
DEXTER MORGAN.
COME AND JOIN ME
ON STAGE, DEXTER.
I KNOW YOU WEREN'T
EXPECTING THIS,
BUT IT'S IMPORTANT.
PLEASE.
Dexter: SO MUCH
FOR SLIPPING OUT QUIETLY.
crowd: DEXTER!
- DEXTER.
THEY WANT YOU, DEXTER.
[crowd slowly
chanting "Dexter!"]
- DEXTER. DEXTER.
DEXTER.
[cheers and applause]
[elevator bell rings]
DEXTER WORKS
WITH MIAMI METRO HOMICIDE.
RECENTLY, HE LOST HIS WIFE.
SHE WAS MURDERED...
[crowd gasps]
BY THE TRINITY KILLER.
[shocked muttering]
THE VERY PERSON THAT DEXTER'S
DEPARTMENT WAS HUNTING.
YOU WERE THE ONE
TO FIND HER, YOUR WIFE?
RITA?
- [whispers] YEAH.
YES.
- I'M GONNA ASK YOU
TO DO SOMETHING, DEXTER,
AND IT'S GONNA BE
VERY DIFFICULT.
I WANT YOU TO RELIVE
THAT MOMENT.
ACCORDING
TO THE NEWSPAPERS,
YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO BE
GOING AWAY ON HONEYMOON?
DEXTER.
- YE--YES.
- TELL US ABOUT IT.
- WELL, WE POSTPONED
THE HONEYMOON
BECAUSE WE HAD
A NEW BABY, A BOY.
- KEEP GOING.
TELL ME HOW YOU FOUND HER.
PLEASE.
- I'D COME HOME
AFTER WORK.
[on TV monitor] I REMEMBER
WALKING THROUGH THE HOUSE.
I TURNED THE CORNER AND...
IT'S LIKE TIME
ACTUALLY SLOWED DOWN
AND THEN STOPPED.
IT'S JUST A SERIES
OF PICTURES.
- WHAT'D YOU SEE?
- I SAW MY SON
SITTING IN BLOOD.
HE WAS CRYING.
SO MUCH BLOOD.
AND SHE WAS THERE
IN THE TUB.
SHE'D BLED OUT.
HER EYES WERE STILL OPEN.
- I WANT YOU TO TELL ME
SOMETHING, DEXTER.
I WANT YOU TO BE
VERY HONEST.
WHAT DID YOU FEEL
IN THAT MOMENT?
WE WANT TO KNOW.
- IT'S DIFFICULT
TO PUT INTO WORDS.
EVERYTHING...
FELL APART. I FELT...
- SHATTERED?
- YES.
- WHEN THE PRIMAL SELF
IS SHATTERED,
IT REACHES OUT IN SEARCH OF
WHAT WILL MAKE IT WHOLE AGAIN.
DO YOU FEEL THAT, DEXTER?
THAT HUNGER INSIDE YOU
TO BE WHOLE AGAIN?
- I DO.
- THAT HUNGER
IS YOUR PRIMAL SELF.
YOU MUST OPEN YOUR HEART
AND LISTEN
TO WHAT IT'S SAYING.
MANY PEOPLE
AFTER SUFFERING A TRAGEDY...
- MR. HARMON?
- SPEND THE REST OF THEIR LIVES
AS BROKEN BEINGS...
- CAN YOU SIGN THIS, PLEASE?
- LIVING IN THE PAST.
[dialing cell phone]
YOUR PRIMAL SELF
IS CRYING OUT TO BE WHOLE.
WHAT IS IT
THAT WILL MAKE YOU WHOLE?
FOR SOME,
IT'S A NEW JOB.
FOR OTHERS, THE LOVE
OF ANOTHER PERSON.
YOUR PRIMAL SELF
WILL TELL YOU,
BUT YOU HAVE TO BE OPEN
TO HEARING THE MESSAGE.
ARE YOU?
- YES.
- THEN YOU'VE JUST TAKEN
YOUR FIRST STEP
TOWARD HAPPINESS.
[cheers and applause]
[cell phone vibrating]
DEXTER.
[lock beeps]
[panting]
[knock at door]
[exhales]
[dialing cell phone]
[screams]
AAH!
[screaming]
- YOU FUCKIN' BITCH!
- [gasping]
- [grunting]
[growls]
- NOT THIS TIME.
[smelling salts snap,
Cole sniffs]
I'M GONNA TAKE THIS GAG
OUT OF YOUR MOUTH,
BUT IF YOU MAKE ONE SOUND
I DON'T LIKE,
I'M GONNA CUT
YOUR EYES OUT.
BLINK SO I KNOW
YOU UNDERSTAND.
WE KNOW ABOUT BOYD
AND DAN THE DENTIST.
AND NOW YOU.
WHO ARE THE OTHERS?
- THE GUY WHO HELD
A WATCH UP TO MY EAR.
"TICK TICK TICK.
THAT'S THE SOUND
OF YOUR LIFE RUNNING OUT."
- WHAT ARE THEIR NAMES?
- [indistinctly whispering]
- WHAT DID HE SAY?
- HUEY, DEWEY,
AND LOUIE.
- LOOK AT THE WOMEN
WHOSE LIVES YOU DESTROYED.
- [groans]
- LOOK.
- [grunting]
- DEATH WAS THE ONLY KINDNESS
YOU SHOWED THEM.
- [groaning]
- IT'S A SHAME
YOU CAN ONLY DIE ONCE.
[Cole grunting]
[groans]
- YOU SAID I'D DONE THIS BEFORE.
THAT'S TRUE.
THIS IS WHO I AM.
WHEN I WAS A CHILD,
MY MOTHER WAS MURDERED
IN FRONT OF ME,
AND IT...
SHATTERED ME.
I'VE DONE THIS EVER SINCE.
BECAUSE
FOR THE LONGEST TIME,
IT WAS THE ONLY WAY
I COULD FEEL...
UNBROKEN.
AND THEN,
RITA WAS KILLED AND
NONE OF THIS
MADE SENSE ANYMORE.
UNTIL NOW.
Dexter:
MIGUEL COULDN'T.
MY FATHER COULDN'T.
CAN ANYONE LIVE WITH THE TRUTH
OF WHAT I AM?
IS LUMEN
WHAT WILL MAKE ME WHOLE?
[elevator bell rings]
- MOVING IN?
- THE LIEUTENANT SAID
I SHOULD BRING SOME OF MY STUFF
INTO THIS DEPARTMENT.
- IT WAS YOU.
LAGUERTA ASKED YOU
TO BACK HER STORY,
AND OF COURSE YOU DID.
- DEB.
- "DEB"?
- DETECTIVE MORGAN,
YOU'RE THE YOUNGEST WOMAN
IN MIAMI METRO
TO EVER MAKE DETECTIVE,
AND I REALLY ADMIRE YOU,
LIKE, A LOT.
AND I CAME HERE HOPING
TO LEARN FROM YOU.
- WHAT YOU DID
YOU WOULD NEVER
LEARN FROM ME.
GOOD LUCK.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED IT.
- DEB.
I'M GONNA DO
WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO SET THE RECORD STRAIGHT.
- I THOUGHT YOU WERE
BACKING LAGUERTA'S STORY.
- NO, I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT I WAS GONNA DO.
I WAS STUCK
BETWEEN A ROCK AND MY WIFE,
BUT I DECIDED
I'M BACKING YOU.
- MIGHT NOT GO OVER
TOO WELL AT HOME.
- HEY, YOU'RE
FLESH AND BLOOD TO ME,
LIKE MY KID SISTER,
BUT BETTER BECAUSE
I ACTUALLY LIKE YOU.
- DAMN.
- IT'S OKAY.
- YEAH.
IT'S OKAY.
- MOST PEOPLE WAIT
UNTIL THE SEMINAR IS OVER
BEFORE CHECKING OUT.
- UH, I LOSE
MY NANNY IN AN HOUR.
I GOTTA GET BACK
TO MY SON.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
- IT'S NOTHING IMPORTANT.
JUST A LITTLE
SECURITY GLITCH.
- MM.
Dexter: LIKE YOUR CHIEF
OF SECURITY'S HEAD
IS IN MY LUGGAGE?
- I WANT TO THANK YOU
FOR COMING ONSTAGE.
- IT DIDN'T SEEM
LIKE I HAD ANY CHOICE.
- I KNOW IT WAS SUDDEN,
AND YOU PROBABLY
DIDN'T APPRECIATE IT,
BUT YOU'LL
LOOK BACK ON IT,
YOU'LL REALIZE
IT WAS WORTH IT.
DON'T FORGET WHAT HAPPENED
HERE THIS WEEKEND, DEXTER.
- I WON'T.
- ACT ON WHAT
YOU'VE LEARNED.
DON'T LET IT SLIP AWAY.
IT'S WHAT I TELL
MY CLIENTS.
TICK TICK TICK?
THAT'S THE SOUND
OF YOUR LIFE RUNNING OUT.
Dexter: MY PRIMAL INSTINCTS
WERE RIGHT.
JORDAN'S ONE OF THEM.
- TAKE IT, DEXTER.
- OH, I WILL.
[cargo door opens]
[thuds]
Dexter: IT'S A LAW
OF PHYSICS
THAT ELEMENTS
WANT TO UNIFY.
SINGLE CELLS
IN A PETRI DISH
THRASH AROUND
UNTIL THEY COALESCE.
[ticket tears]
AND EVENTS IN THE UNIVERSE
THAT ONCE SEEMED RANDOM
ARE EVENTUALLY REVEALED TO HAVE
AN UNDERLYING CONNECTEDNESS.
- JORDAN CHASE IS ONE OF THEM.
I'M SURE OF IT.
"TICK TICK TICK."
- BUT HE WASN'T
IN THE PHOTO.
- MAYBE HE TOOK THE PHOTO,
I DON'T KNOW.
- WE'RE GONNA TAKE DOWN
JORDAN CHASE?
[splash]
- FIRST THINGS FIRST.
- JUST...LET GO?
[water bubbling]
[exhales]
- JUST LET GO.
[camera whirrs]