- PREVIOUSLY, ON DEXTER...
RITA'S INSIDE.
IT WAS ME.
- FBI?
FUCKING BUNCH OF IDIOTS.
- YOU WANT TO TALK TO DEXTER,
SCHEDULE AN APPOINTMENT.
- I'LL DO THAT.
- IF THIS WERE
ANYONE BUT DEXTER,
WE'D AT LEAST BE THINKING
LIKE DETECTIVES.
WHEN THE WIFE IS DEAD,
90% OF THE TIME,
THE HUSBAND DID IT.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU WANNA TALK ABOUT IT,
OR YOU JUST GONNA ACT WEIRD?
- THERE'S NOTHING
TO TALK ABOUT.
- ALL RITA AND I
EVER DID WAS KISS.
DEXTER FOUND OUT
ABOUT THE INDISCRETION,
AND, UH, CAME OVER
AND PUNCHED ME OUT.
- ARTHUR MITCHELL.
- KYLE BUTLER.
- AND WHAT'S HIS NAME?
- UH, KYLE BUTLER.
- SOMETHING HAPPENED...
TO YOUR MOM.
- SHE'S DEAD!
AND IT DOESN'T EVEN MATTER
TO YOU!
I WISH YOU WERE DEAD!
- I JUST GOT A CALL
FROM THE FBI.
ABOUT YOUR BROTHER'S
INTERVIEW.
- DON'T TELL ME.
WHAT'D HE SAY?
- HE DIDN'T SHOW.
- I DON'T KNOW WHERE
THE FUCK YOU ARE
OR WHY YOU THINK YOU CAN FUCKING
RUN AWAY FROM THE FBI,
BUT YOU BETTER
GET BACK HERE BEF--
[beep]
- MY WIFE DIED,
AND IT WAS MY FAULT.
- YOUR DEAD WIFE
CAN SUCK MY DICK.
- THAT'S THE FIRST HUMAN THING
I'VE SEEN YOU DO
SINCE SHE DIED, DEXTER.
THEY'RE NOT BETTER OFF
WITHOUT YOU.
YOU'RE NOT BETTER OFF
WITHOUT THEM.
YOU NEED TO GO BACK.
[quirky music]
* *
- IT'S SAID THERE ARE
SEVEN STAGES OF GRIEF.
I SUPPOSE KILLING SOMEONE
WITH MY BARE HANDS
IN A MEN'S ROOM
WAS MY WAY OF WORKING
THROUGH THE ANGER STAGE.
WHATEVER THE OTHER
SIX STAGES ARE...
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THEM.
'CAUSE NOW
I'M A FULL-TIME DAD.
ONCE THE KIDS AND I
ARE BACK TOGETHER,
IT'LL ALL BE FINE.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE WE'RE
ALL GONNA SQUISH IN HERE.
- IT'S JUST TEMPORARY,
TILL WE CAN GET A NEW PLACE.
- HERE...
HE NEEDS TO BE
HOSED OFF OR SOMETHING.
HEY.
WELCOME HOME.
- THIS ISN'T OUR HOME.
AND WHY DO WE NEED
A NEW PLACE, ANYWAY?
- I THINK STARTING
IN A NEW APARTMENT
WILL BE GOOD FOR US.
LOOK, I FOUND A PLACE
PRACTICALLY ON THE BEACH.
OR ANOTHER ONE
RIGHT NEXT TO A PARK.
- BUT, UNTIL THEN, ASTOR,
YOU GET TO SHARE
THE BED WITH ME.
AND, DEX,
YOU'RE ON THE COUCH.
CODY, YOU'RE ON THE COT.
- TIME FOR YOU BOTH
TO GET TO BED--SCHOOL TOMORROW.
- HOW CAN I GO TO SCHOOL?
I DON'T EVEN HAVE
ANY OF MY THINGS.
- [crying]
- MAKE A LIST.
I'LL GO BY THE HOUSE TOMORROW.
- I WANT TO GO WITH YOU.
- I DON'T THINK
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
- WHY?
- WELL...
BECAUSE OF WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR MOTHER THERE.
- I KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
TO MY MOM.
SHE WAS MURDERED.
- DON'T FORGET,
9 A.M. TOMORROW.
FBI INTERVIEW.
- [crying]
- ONE FINAL LOOSE END
TO TIE UP
BEFORE PUTTING
ALL THIS BEHIND ME.
- AT THE TIME
OF YOUR WIFE'S DEATH,
YOU WERE...
- I ALREADY TOLD YOU.
I WAS ON MY BOAT.
- RIGHT.
JUST SEEMED ODD.
YOU DO A LOT OF NIGHT BOATING,
MR. MORGAN?
- SOMETIMES.
IT'S MORE PEACEFUL.
- AND YOU WERE BY YOURSELF?
- YES, I WAS ALONE.
THERE'S SECURITY CAMERAS
AT THE MARINA.
YOU CAN SEE ME LEAVING
AND RETURNING.
- WE'VE SEEN THE FOOTAGE,
MR. MORGAN.
THE PROBLEM IS, ACCORDING
TO THE CORONER'S REPORT,
YOUR WIFE
WAS KILLED SEVERAL HOURS
BEFORE YOU GOT ON THE BOAT.
- IS THAT WHAT THIS IS ABOUT?
YOU FUCKING SERIOUS?
SUGGESTING I HAVE ANYTHING TO DO
WITH MY WIFE'S DEATH...
THAT I'D SLICE HER ARTERY,
LET HER BLEED OUT
IN THE BATHROOM--
- MR. MORGAN,
WE KNOW THAT YOU WERE
AT ARTHUR MITCHELL'S HOUSE.
AT THE TIME
OF YOUR WIFE'S DEATH,
YOU WERE PART OF THE TEAM
THAT RAIDED
ARTHUR MITCHELL'S HOUSE.
- [sighs]
RIGHT, OF COURSE.
- WE KNOW YOU DIDN'T
KILL YOUR WIFE.
- WE'RE JUST LOOKING
FOR A REASON
WHY ARTHUR MITCHELL
MIGHT HAVE TARGETED HER.
- BECAUSE
HE'S A SERIAL KILLER?
- HOW'D IT GO?
- IT'S...FINE.
I'M JUST GLAD IT'S OVER,
AND I CAN MOVE ON.
- WE MISS YOU, BROTHER.
- YEAH?
HOW'S HANDLING THE DEPARTMENT
ALL BY YOURSELF?
- AH, IT'S A BREEZE.
- I'LL BE BACK
IN A FEW DAYS.
- OH, NO, YOU WON'T.
YOU'RE TAKING
AT LEAST ANOTHER WEEK.
YOU NEED TO SPEND TIME
WITH YOUR FAMILY.
- THANKS.
- EXCUSE ME.
- ANYTHING YOU NEED, DEXTER,
JUST ASK.
- I WILL.
SEE YOU TONIGHT.
OH, GRANDPARENTS
STOPPING BY TOO.
- THEY'RE ALL STAYING
AT YOUR PLACE?
- YEAH.
IT'S CROWDED.
BUT IT'S TEMPORARY.
HE JUST DOESN'T WANT
THE KIDS STAYING AT THE HOUSE
WHERE THEIR MOM...
- RIGHT.
- SO...WE ALL GOOD HERE?
- YEAH, HE'S AIRTIGHT.
BUT OTHERWISE,
WE GOT JACK SHIT.
ARTHUR MITCHELL DISAPPEARED.
THE ONLY LEAD WE HAVE NOW
IS THIS KYLE BUTLER.
- WE HAD A MURDER VICTIM
BY THAT NAME
A FEW WEEKS BACK.
- WELL, OUR GUY'S ALIVE,
AS FAR AS WE KNOW.
UNFORTUNATELY,
HE'S DISAPPEARED AS WELL.
WE'RE GONNA
HAVE A SKETCH ARTIST
MEET WITH THE FAMILY,
AND GET A COMPOSITE OF HIM.
- OKAY.
WELL, I'D APPRECIATE IT
IF YOU'D KEEP ME POSTED.
- WILL DO.
- OH, HEY.
MARIA, YOUR MAIL.
¿PERO QUE CONO?
- SO, DEXTER MORGAN,
LET'S GET YOU A MOVING VAN.
AREN'T YOU A CUTE KID, HUH?
HUH?
[laughs]
- HE'S NOT ACTUALLY
TALKING YET.
HERE'S YOUR 18-FOOTER.
WHAT'S HIS NAME?
- HARRISON.
- 14-FOOTER.
IT'S A FAMILY NAME?
- BLOOD.
UH, SORT OF.
- SO WHAT KIND OF STUFF
YOU MOVING?
- JUST, UH, FURNITURE,
CLOTHES.
UH, DRESSER, MAYBE.
PLENTY OF REASONS
FOR BLOOD TO BE THERE.
SOMEONE CUT HIMSELF MOVING...
- WELL, IF THAT'S ALL
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT,
SAVE YOURSELF SOME MONEY,
GO WITH THE 10-FOOTER.
- [sighs]
I CAN'T
LET MYSELF THINK ABOUT THIS.
I'VE JUST GOT
TO MOVE THE KIDS.
ACTUALLY, I THINK I'LL GO
WITH THE 14-FOOTER.
- OKAY, LET'S, UH,
WRITE YOU UP.
- [grunts]
[makes quacking noise]
[clattering]
WE'RE GONNA GET
A MUCH BETTER PLACE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK,
CLOSER TO THE PARK
OR THE BEACH?
[clattering]
- HELLO?
[knocking]
DEXTER?
- NO ANNOYING NEIGHBORS.
- HEY, DEX.
- BROUGHT YOUR MAIL.
- THANKS.
WOW, LOOK AT HARRISON.
BOY, HE'S JUST GETTING BIGGER
EVERY DAY.
HEY, LOOK, DEX, UM...
YOU KNOW, WE HAVEN'T
HAD A CHANCE TO TALK.
BUT I JUST--
I WANTED TO LET YOU KNOW
HOW SORRY I AM
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
- THANKS.
- HAVE THEY CAUGHT
THE TRINITY KILLER YET OR--
- [sighs] NO.
- [sighs]
MAN, IF I COULD JUST
GET MY HANDS ON HIM.
- I CAN ONLY IMAGINE.
- HEY, LISTEN, YOU KNOW,
I KNOW WE'VE
HAD OUR DIFFERENCES,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
I'M A SINGLE DAD.
I MEAN, I KNOW THE ROPES, SO...
IF YOU NEED ANY HELP--
- NO, I'M GOOD.
- 'CAUSE, YOU KNOW,
YOU GOTTA GIVE UP A LOT.
I MEAN, I ACTUALLY HAVE A PRETTY
DECENT CAREER GOING, YOU KNOW.
BUT I HAD TO TURN DOWN
SOME MAJOR JOB OFFERS
SO I COULD JUST
WORK AT HOME
AND JUST, YOU KNOW,
BE THERE FOR THOSE KIDS.
- GOOD FOR YOU.
- I MEAN, FORGET
ABOUT ANY FREE TIME.
OR ANY LIFE OF YOUR OWN,
REALLY.
I MEAN, YOU JUST, YOU KNOW,
YOU HAVE TO BE THERE.
RIGHT? EVERY MORNING.
EVERY EVENING.
EVERY WEEKEND.
YOU READY TO DO THAT, DEX,
FOR THE KIDS?
- YES, ELLIOT,
I'M READY TO DO THAT.
FOR THE KIDS.
- WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
HERE, LET ME--
- NO! I GOT IT.
- OKAY, WELL...
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT WORKS OUT.
IT REALLY DOES, YOU KNOW.
I MEAN, YEAH, YOU HAVE
TO GIVE UP YOUR LIFE AND ALL,
BUT, UH...YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU JUST--YOU LIVE
FOR THOSE KIDS,
AND...IT'S SATISFYING.
- EXCUSE ME.
- YEAH.
- [clears throat]
I'LL BE A GOOD FATHER.
EVERYONE MAKES SACRIFICES.
I CAN TOO.
FOCUS ON THE KIDS.
- WOW, I DIDN'T KNOW YOU
WERE GONNA BRING SO MUCH.
YOU CAN JUST PUT THAT...
- [grunts]
- RIGHT THERE IS GREAT.
- I EMPTIED THE REFRIGERATOR.
SOMEONE LEFT
ANOTHER CAKE AT THE DOOR.
- I JUST ATE
A WHOLE TUNA CASSEROLE
TO MAKE ROOM IN THE APARTMENT.
CODY, THIS IS A GOOD JOB
FOR YOU.
WANNA HELP ME
UNLOAD THE FOOD?
- OKAY.
- WOW. YOU SURE DO HAVE
A LOT OF BEER, AUNT DEB.
[Deb chuckles]
- UH...
PEOPLE JUST KEEP BRINGING IT.
HEH.
- THIS IS ALL YOU BROUGHT?
- UH, WELL, WE'RE A LITTLE
SHORT ON SPACE.
- YOU DIDN'T EVEN
BRING THE RIGHT CLOTHES.
THIS IS MY REJECT STUFF.
I CAN'T WEAR
ANY OF THIS TO SCHOOL.
- ASTOR, COME ON.
NO ONE'S GONNA NOTICE YOU.
- [gasps]
- UHH, OKAY.
HONEY, WOULD YOU
HOLD THE BABY?
- COME HERE.
- CODY.
WHY DON'T YOU HELP US
CARRY THE LAST LOAD IN, HMM?
- I LIKE IT HERE.
IT'S LIKE CAMPING.
- EXACTLY.
BOYS ARE EASIER.
IT DOESN'T MATTER HOW MUCH
I LOVE MY CHILDREN,
I'M STILL A CREATURE
OF THE NIGHT.
[Harrison fussing]
- CAN'T SLEEP EITHER?
THE BLOOD
PROBABLY MEANS NOTHING.
SOMEONE CUT THEIR FINGER
WHILE MOVING.
BUT I WON'T BE ABLE
TO PUT IT OUT OF MY MIND
UNTIL I KNOW FOR SURE.
[truck door rattling]
[spraying]
- SOMEONE DID
A QUICK CLEANUP JOB
BUT FORGOT
TO WASH THE DOOR.
[baby coos]
[whispering]
YEAH, IT'S PRETTY.
I KNOW.
BUT NOT THE STORY
IT TELLS.
ONCE UPON A TIME,
AN EVIL GREEN OGRE
LEFT A CIRCULAR SPATTER
AT THREE FEET HIGH,
CONSISTENT WITH
BLUNT FORCE TRAUMA...
WHICH SEEMS TO INDICATE
THE HANDSOME YOUNG PRINCE
WAS HIT WHILE ON HIS KNEES,
AT LEAST TWO OR THREE TIMES.
OR THE PRINCESS
WAS ON HER KNEES.
SMALL HANDS.
FEMALE.
[sighs]
- I THOUGHT THE KIDS WERE
YOUR NUMBER ONE RESPONSIBILITY.
- THEY ARE.
- BUT HERE YOU ARE...
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.
- IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE.
- IT NEVER IS.
- IT'S LIKE WHEN
YOU GET ON A PLANE.
THEY TELL YOU
IF THE OXYGEN MASKS COME DOWN
TO PUT YOURS ON FIRST
BEFORE HELPING THE KIDS.
I HAVE TO TAKE CARE
OF MY OWN NEEDS TOO.
OTHERWISE, I RISK
SPINNING OUT OF CONTROL.
AND THAT'S NOT GOOD
FOR ANYONE.
- I'M NOT JUST SAYING THIS
FOR THE SAKE OF THE KIDS, DEX,
BUT FOR YOU.
THEY'RE NOT ONLY
YOUR RESPONSIBILITY.
THEY'RE YOUR SALVATION.
- I HAVE TO GIVE HIM
A BOTTLE.
NO REASON
A TRUCK RENTAL AGENCY
WOULD PUT ANY SERIOUS
SAFEGUARDS ON THEIR RECORDS.
THE TRUCK WAS MOST RECENTLY
RENTED TO BOYD FOWLER.
BOYD SEEMS TO HAVE
LISTED HIS ADDRESS
AS THE DEPARTMENT
OF SANITATION.
NO HOME ADDRESS.
MIAMI/DADE COUNTY DEPARTMENT
OF SANITATION,
DIVISION OF
DEAD ANIMAL PICKUP,
MEANING THE BLOOD BELONGS
TO AN ANIMAL.
BUT WHAT ABOUT THOSE
LITTLE HANDPRINTS?
TWO LINES.
HUMAN.
- WELL, WELL, WELL.
WHAT DO WE GOT HERE?
- RACCOON.
- YOU CALL THIS IN?
- YEAH, I DID.
I WAS DRIVING DOWN THE ROAD,
AND...I SAW IT.
KIND OF CREEPS ME OUT.
YOU'RE PROBABLY USED TO
SEEING DEAD THINGS, THOUGH, HUH?
- CAN'T SAY I EVER
GET USED TO IT.
- I DON'T USUALLY
COME THIS WAY,
BUT I'M IN THE MIDDLE
OF MOVING TO A NEW PLACE.
IT'S A HASSLE, HUH?
MOVING?
- I WOULDN'T KNOW.
- NO?
- LIVED IN THE SAME HOUSE
FOR OVER 20 YEARS.
- SO WHY DID YOU
RENT A MOVING VAN?
- HELLO THERE, BANDIT.
THIS DON'T LOOK RIGHT.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- WELL, USUALLY, YOU FIND
A DEAD ANIMAL IN THE ROAD,
IT MEANS
HE WAS HIT BY A CAR.
BUT THERE'S NO TIRE MARKS
OR BLOOD ON THE ASPHALT.
THIS RACCOON WAS KILLED
SOMEPLACE ELSE AND DROPPED HERE.
- HE'S CSI-ing ME.
- HE'S GOT
DEFENSIVE WOUNDS ON HIS PAWS.
LITTLE GUY PUT UP
QUITE A STRUGGLE.
ALL RIGHTY THEN.
[engine starts]
- HE'S DEFINITELY PECULIAR.
BUT I GUESS
THE BEST AND BRIGHTEST
DON'T TYPICALLY GET INTO
DEAD ANIMAL PICKUP.
[indistinct chatter]
- JUST SO YOU KNOW, OKAY?
- WHAT DO WE GOT?
- WE GOT A FEMALE VICTIM.
PART OF
A FEMALE VICTIM.
- PART?
- WE GOT A HEAD.
- JUST A HEAD?
- YEAH.
DECAPITATION.
PROBABLY SOME KIND
OF DRUG KILLING.
- NICE.
LET ME ASK YOU A QUESTION,
HYPOTHETICAL.
SAY A NEWLY-MARRIED PERSON...
- MM-HMM.
- ACCIDENTALLY DISCOVERS
THAT HIS OR HER NEW SPOUSE
HAS A SAVINGS ACCOUNT
WITH A LOT OF MONEY.
IS THAT SOMETHING THAT ONE
SHOULD EXPECT TO SHARE?
- FUCK, NO.
THAT'S YOUR MONEY.
YOU TELL THE LIEUTENANT TO KEEP
HER FUCKIN' HANDS OFF IT.
- TAKE ME TO THE HEAD.
- ALL RIGHT.
[indistinct chatter]
- SHE WAS STILL ALIVE
WHEN THEY CUT HER HEAD OFF.
EXCISION OF EYES AND TONGUE
WAS DONE POSTMORTEM.
- THAT'S CONSIDERATE OF THEM.
- YOU WERE RIGHT.
IT'S JUST A HEAD.
- UNLESS THEY BURIED HER
STANDING UP.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- JUST TRYING TO HELP.
YOU'RE LOOKING A LITTLE RAGGED.
- I'M EXHAUSTED.
THERE ARE FIVE PEOPLE
IN MY TINY APARTMENT.
I SHARED A BED
WITH ASTOR LAST NIGHT,
AND SHE KICKED ME
ALL NIGHT LONG.
- YOU KNOW, YOU'RE WELCOME
TO CRASH AT MY PLACE,
IF YOU WANT.
- UH, NO THANKS, DETECTIVE.
- OKAY.
- IT LOOKS LIKE SANTA MUERTE.
- WHAT?
- SANTA MUERTE, THE CULT.
"SAINT DEATH."
- YEAH, I KNOW WHAT IT IS,
BUT WHY DO YOU SAY THAT?
- WELL, THE MISSING EYES
AND TONGUE
WERE MEANT TO SEND A MESSAGE.
YOU DIDN'T SEE ANYTHING,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA SAY ANYTHING.
- WHO ARE YOU?
- OFFICER MANZON.
CIRA.
THE GOLDEN CANDLES MEAN MONEY.
THE ICONS, I DON'T KNOW.
THERE'S SO MANY NOW, YOU...
MIGHT NEED AN EXPERT ON IT.
- AND YOU KNOW
ALL OF THIS BECAUSE...
- IT'S MY NEIGHBORHOOD.
AND IF IT IS
SANTA MUERTE...
THEY USED A MACHETE ON HER.
- OKAY, WELL,
WE'LL KEEP THAT IN MIND.
BUT THIS PARK IS
A LOCAL DRUG HANGOUT,
AND DRUG CARTELS
LIKE TO CUT HEADS OFF.
SO WE MIGHT
FOLLOW THAT LEAD.
- OF COURSE.
- HEY...WE FOUND THE BODY
ON THE OTHER END OF THE PARK,
UNDER SOME BUSHES, NO I.D.
GOTTA CANVASS THE NEIGHBORHOOD,
START ASKING QUESTIONS.
- NO ONE WILL TALK.
THEY'RE TOO AFRAID.
- WELL, WE STILL ASK,
OFFICER.
- "HELPING YOUR CHILDREN
COPE WITH GRIEF."
"GRANDPA'S GONE TO HEAVEN."
"SAYING GOOD-BYE TO FLUFFY."
BUT NOTHING ON
"MOMMY BLED OUT IN A BATHTUB."
BOYD FOWLER,
YOU HAVE A PRISON RECORD.
ASSAULT WITH A DEADLY WEAPON.
18 MONTHS AT OKEECHOBEE.
YOU SAID YOU LIVED IN A HOUSE,
BUT THERE ARE NO MORTGAGE
RECORDS IN YOUR NAME.
IN THE SAME HOUSE
FOR OVER 20 YEARS.
YOU INHERITED IT
FROM YOUR PARENTS,
RICH AND ELSIE FOWLER
IN OPA-LOCKA.
[keys rattling in door]
HEY.
HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
- A WHOLE AFTERNOON GETTING
DOORS SHUT IN MY FACE.
- SORRY.
- YOU?
- OKAY.
WE FINISHED LAGUERTA'S
CASEROLA DE CAMARONES
AND MASUKA'S
CHOCOLATE LAVA CAKE,
AND ASTOR TOLD ME
SHE HATED LIVING HERE.
THEY'RE BOTH
ASLEEP IN THE BED.
LOOKING AT APARTMENTS.
- SO IT'S EVERYTHING
AS USUAL.
- [sighs]
THEY'RE SEEING
A GRIEF COUNSELOR TOMORROW.
- MAYBE THAT'LL HELP.
STILL, EVEN AFTER...
- WHAT?
- YOU'RE GONNA BE
A SINGLE DAD
RAISING THREE KIDS.
GONNA BE HARD.
RITA WAS A GREAT MOM.
- THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO
TO MAKE UP FOR THAT.
BUT I'M GONNA HAVE TO TRY.
- WELL, I'LL BE HERE.
YOU CAN COUNT ON ME.
THE KIDS'LL BE OKAY.
I KNOW THAT PLACE.
IT'S NEAR THE STATION.
THEY HAVE AN OPEN HOUSE
TOMORROW.
MAYBE I'LL CHECK IT OUT
FOR YOU.
- GREAT.
YOU WANT THE COUCH TONIGHT?
- NO, YOU TAKE IT.
[numbers beeping]
[line ringing]
- HEY.
- HI.
- GLAD YOU CALLED.
- HEY, FUCK PUDDLE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- JUST GIVING YOU
A KISS HELLO.
- I-I CAME OVER HERE
TO SLEEP,
NOT TO HAVE YOUR FAT LITTLE
SAUSAGE FINGERS ALL OVER ME.
- [chuckles]
THERE'S NO ROOM FOR ME
AT MY OWN PLACE.
UNLESS I WANT TO CURL UP INSIDE
A FUCKIN' TOASTER OVEN.
[grunts]
I'M TRYING SO HARD
TO BE A GOOD SISTER,
'CAUSE FUCK KNOWS, DEXTER'S
ALWAYS BEEN THE BEST BROTHER.
BUT...IT IS
FUCKING EXHAUSTING.
- I'M SURE.
WELL, LOOK,
YOU'RE, UH,
WELCOME TO STAY HERE
FOR AS LONG AS YOU WANT,
WHENEVER YOU WANT.
AND I PROMISE TO KEEP MY FAT
LITTLE SAUSAGE FINGERS OFF YOU.
- YOU BETTER.
- HOW'S YOUR BROTHER?
- YOU KNOW.
- I HEARD THE FBI INTERVIEW
WENT WELL.
I MEAN, THAT MUST
BE A LOAD OFF.
- WHY WOULD
THAT BE A LOAD OFF?
- [scoffs] NOTHIN'.
NEVER MIND.
- THEY'RE LOOKING FOR SOMEONE
NAMED KYLE BUTLER
WHO'S A FRIEND
OF ARTHUR MITCHELL'S.
THEY THINK
IF THEY CAN FIND HIM,
THEN HE CAN LEAD THEM
TO MITCHELL.
- BUT THEY CAN'T FIND HIM?
- WELL, NOT YET.
THEY'RE HAVING SKETCHES DONE.
THEY'RE TRYING TO GET
A POSITIVE I.D.
- KYLE BUTLER.
WHY DOES THAT NAME
SOUND SO FAMILIAR?
- WELL, THAT'S
THE WEIRD THING.
WE WORKED THAT CASE,
REMEMBER?
A DEAD KYLE BUTLER.
- RIGHT, HE GOT HIS HEAD
SMASHED IN.
WENT UNSOLVED.
ANY CONNECTION?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I'M SURE THE FBI WILL
FIND A WAY TO FUCK IT UP.
WILL YOU GET THE LIGHTS?
- YES, MA'AM.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO
FOR THE NEXT BATCH?
MICKEY MOUSE, SILVER DOLLAR?
GREAT BIG ONES?
- TRIANGLES.
- A CHALLENGE.
[sizzling]
- DEXTER'S MAKING
TRIANGLE PANCAKES.
- ACTUALLY,
THEY'RE MORE FREEFORM.
WANNA SET THE TABLE
FOR US?
- UH, SURE.
THEY'RE JUST BLOBS.
- HOW DARE YOU?
- TRIANGLES.
[laughing]
- I COUNTED TOO MANY PLATES.
- MOM'S NOT HERE.
- THAT'S OKAY.
- NO, IT'S NOT.
SHE SHOULD BE HERE.
- I'M SORRY.
- THAT DOESN'T
MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
- ASTOR, I'M DOING
THE BEST I CAN HERE.
LET'S JUST...SIT DOWN
AND HAVE SOME BREAKFAST.
- I DON'T WANT TO!
I WANNA GO BACK HOME!
- ASTOR--
- STOP IT!
- YEAH, JUST STOP IT!
- BOTH OF YOU JUST STOP
FIGHTING ALL THE TIME!
I HATE IT!
[door slams]
- WHILE THEY'RE SEEING
THE GRIEF COUNSELOR,
I'LL BE GETTING
MY OWN KIND OF THERAPY.
- SO IS THIS, UH...
SOMETHING WE SHOULD
TALK ABOUT?
WHATEVER'S GOING ON
BETWEEN US?
- NO.
- I MEAN...
WE HAVE SEX ONE DAY,
AND THEN--
- I'M SORRY,
I'M NOT THE KIND OF PERSON
WHO WOULD EVER
HAVE SEX WITH YOU.
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT WE'RE DOING.
- WE'RE NOT DOING ANYTHING.
WE NEVER DID DO ANYTHING.
WE NEVER WILL
DO ANYTHING.
- SO WE NEVER HAD SEX?
- EXACTLY.
- THAT'S REALLY WEIRD.
'CAUSE I REMEMBER--
- I GOTTA GO NOW.
I'M GONNA GO.
- [scoffs]
[door closes]
- HOW'S IT GOING?
- I HATE THIS SHIT.
[clatter]
[grunts]
THIS IS DEXTER'S JOB.
BLOOD. IT'S GROSS.
WELL, WHOEVER
CUT THE HEAD OFF
USED THE SAME WEAPON TO CUT
THE EYES AND THE TONGUE OUT.
BUT I CAN'T FIND
ANYTHING THAT FITS.
I MEAN, I'VE TRIED TWO SWORDS,
THREE KNIVES.
- HEY...TRY THE MACHETE.
YEAH.
- HUH.
I THINK WE HAVE A MATCH.
- I'LL SEND SOMEBODY
OVER THERE RIGHT AWAY.
OKAY, YEAH.
HOW'S IT GOING IN THERE?
- MASUKA SAID HE REALLY
LIKES WORKING WITH THE BLOOD.
HE HOPES HE CAN GET
MORE ASSIGNMENTS LIKE THIS.
- I'LL KEEP THAT IN MIND.
LET ME ASK YOU A QUESTION.
- IF YOU WERE MARRIED...
AND YOU FOUND OUT
THAT THE PERSON
YOU WERE MARRIED TO
HAD A SECRET BANK ACCOUNT
WITH A LOT OF MONEY,
YOU THINK THAT PERSON
SHOULD SHARE IT?
- JESUS, ANGEL.
JUST BECAUSE YOU MARRIED HER
DOESN'T MEAN YOU OWN HER.
IT'S HER MONEY.
END OF STORY.
- WELL, YOU GOT A DEAD BODY
WAITING FOR YOU.
[indistinct chatter]
- OH, FUCK ME.
WHY COULDN'T HE HAVE
JUST HANGED HIMSELF,
TOOK SOME PILLS...
STUCK HIS HEAD IN THE OVEN?
PEOPLE ARE SO RUDE.
EXCUSE ME.
- YOU AGAIN.
- IT'S MY NEIGHBORHOOD.
- YOU WERE RIGHT
ABOUT THE MACHETE.
- GOOD...I GUESS.
[camera shutter clicking]
- SO WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?
- WELL, GOLLY GEE, DEB,
I THINK WE GOT
A SHOTGUN WOUND TO THE HEAD.
APPROXIMATELY 24 HOURS AGO.
- MAKE SURE
YOU SWAB THE GUN.
AND CHECK HIS HANDS FOR GSR.
- I GOT IT, I GOT IT.
- I'M JUST CHECKING.
DEXTER USUALLY
WORKS CASES LIKE THIS.
DO WE HAVE AN I.D.?
- ACCORDING TO THIS,
FRANCISCO ALFARO.
HEY, CAN WE ROLL HIM OVER?
- [sighs]
OH, LOOKS LIKE HIS FACE
HAS CHANGED A LITTLE
SINCE HIS DRIVER'S LICENSE
PICTURE WAS TAKEN.
- LOOKS LIKE HIM.
HEY...CHECK OUT THE GIRL.
- WHAT?
- LOOK AT HER.
IMAGINE SHE HAS NO EYES
AND NO TONGUE.
- HOLY SHIT.
- IT'S HER, ISN'T IT?
- THOSE ARE THE EXACT
SAME EARRINGS.
WE'VE GOT OUR HEAD.
- UH-HUH.
BINGO--LOOKS LIKE WE GOT
A MURDER-SUICIDE HERE.
- HOW YOU FIGURE?
- WELL...
GUY GETS PISSED AT HIS WIFE.
CUTS HER HEAD OFF.
LEAVES IT IN THE PARK
FOR EVERYONE TO SEE
AND COMES HOME,
BLOWS HIS HEAD OFF.
- MASUKA, WE GOT SOME
BRAIN GOO ON THE CEILING
YOU NEED TO PHOTOGRAPH.
- OH, FUCK ME
UP THE GOAT ASS.
- WHAT ABOUT ALL THAT
SANTA MUERTE STUFF THEN?
- YEAH...THERE IS
NO SANTA MUERTE STUFF.
- THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
THERE WAS AT THE PARK.
THERE WAS, UH, MISSING EYES
AND A TONGUE
AND THE GOLD CANDLES
AND THE ICONS.
THERE'S NONE OF THAT HERE.
- NO.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
- WHO'S SHE?
- [sighs]
HEY...WHEN IS DEXTER
COMING BACK?
- BOYD FOWLER WORKS
THE 7:00 TO 4:00 SHIFT...
WHICH GIVES ME TIME
TO CHECK OUT HIS HOUSE,
SEE IF THERE'S ANYTHING
THAT'LL PUT HIM ON MY TABLE.
- LET ME GUESS.
THIS IS YOU PUTTING ON
YOUR OXYGEN MASK FIRST.
- BEING ON THE HUNT
KEEPS ME SHARP.
FOCUSED.
THUS, THE BETTER
KILLER I AM,
THE BETTER FATHER.
[flies buzzing]
- SO HE TAKES HIS WORK
HOME WITH HIM.
NO CRIME IN THAT.
A MAN OF SIMPLE TASTE.
LOOKS LIKE
MY GRANDMOTHER'S HOUSE.
A LOADED HANDGUN.
A NO-NO
FOR A CONVICTED FELON.
BUT EVEN SO,
NOT MUCH TO GO ON.
BOYD, YOU ARE VERY BORING.
[whispers] SHIT.
BOYD COMES HOME FOR LUNCH.
OKAY, THAT'S INTERESTING.
[door latch clicks]
- [voice on CD] DO YOU WANT
TO HAVE CONTROL OF YOUR LIFE?
YOU HAVE THAT POWER.
YOU JUST HAVE TO LEARN
HOW TO USE IT.
YOU CAN MAKE UP
ALL THE EXCUSES YOU WANT.
YOU'RE TOO TIRED.
- WHO KEEPS THEIR ATTIC DOOR
LOCKED?
- TOO OLD.
TOO FAT.
TOO STUPID.
[chuckles] YOU KNOW,
I'VE HEARD THEM ALL.
- CHICKEN NOODLE,
CHICKEN NOODLE, CHICKEN NOODLE.
WHERE'S THE TOMATO?
BUT IF YOU WANT SOMETHING...
both: TAKE IT!
- YOU WANT THAT JOB?
both: WELL, THEN, TAKE IT!
- IT'S ENTIRELY UP TO YOU.
THE WORLD DOES NOT PUT ONE...
[cans clattering]
YOU WANT THAT NICE HOUSE
ON THE BEACH?
both: TAKE IT!
- THE WORLD
DOES NOT PUT LIMITATIONS
ON WHAT YOU CAN HAVE.
BUT IF YOU WANT SOMETHING...
both: TAKE IT!
- YOU HAVE THAT POWER.
- I CAN SEE HAVING
AN OLD GIRLFRIEND'S
LOCK OF HAIR...
BUT IDENTIFIED
ONLY BY A NUMBER?
- WE ARE OUR OWN WORST ENEMY.
MAKE NO MISTAKE ABOUT IT.
BUT WITH
A FEW SIMPLE STEPS,
I CAN TEACH YOU HOW TO TAKE
CONTROL OF YOUR LIFE.
TAKE IT!
- ALL I'M SAYING...
IF A WOMAN
PISSED ME OFF ENOUGH,
YEAH, I'D WANNA
CUT HER HEAD OFF.
- WELL,
THAT'S GREAT TO HEAR.
- NO, I'M NOT SAYING
I WOULD DO IT.
BUT I UNDERSTAND THE IMPULSE.
WHAT ARE WE DOING HERE?
- I TOLD DEXTER I'D
CHECK THIS PLACE OUT FOR HIM.
- OH! COME IN, COME IN.
- HEY.
- HI!
UM, WE'VE JUST PAINTED
AND INSTALLED NEW FLOORING
THROUGHOUT THE HOUSE.
- LOOKS GREAT.
- [squeals]
LOTS OF YOUNG COUPLES
IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
AND THE ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
IS ABOUT THREE BLOCKS AWAY.
I'M SURE YOU'D BE
VERY HAPPY HERE.
- OH, IT'S NOT FOR US.
- I THINK WE'D BE
VERY HAPPY HERE TOO.
THANK YOU.
- WELL, I HAVE TO GET
A FEW THINGS OUT OF MY CAR.
BUT IF YOU
HAVE ANY QUESTIONS,
I'LL JUST BE RIGHT OUTSIDE.
- OKAY.
- THANK YOU.
- IT'S A NICE KITCHEN.
- UH-HUH.
- DECENT APPLIANCES.
- OH, LOOK AT THIS.
GREAT BEDROOM.
CHECK IT OUT.
- DON'T.
- OHH.
WOW.
COMFY BED.
FEEL IT.
- GET OFF THE BED.
- WHAT DO YOU SAY?
A LITTLE NAP TIME?
- I'M LEAVING.
- WHAT DID I DO?
- I'VE GOT TO DROP YOU OFF
AT THE STATION,
THEN PICK UP
MY BROTHER'S KIDS.
- HOW DESPERATE AM I
TO FOLLOW BOYD
TO THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE
WHEN ALL I'VE GOT
IS A BIT OF BLOOD
AND A LOCK OF HAIR?
BUT WITH NOTHING ELSE
TO GO ON...
IT'S A RULE OF NATURE.
LEAVE SOME OLD BEDSPRINGS
OUT IN THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE,
AND SOON, IT'LL BE JOINED
BY A REFRIGERATOR,
COUCH, CAR ENGINE.
AND NOW, A BARREL, MOST LIKELY
HOLDING DEAD ANIMALS.
TOO LAZY TO DRIVE IT BACK
TO THE INCINERATOR, I SUPPOSE.
[cell phone ringing]
HEY, DEB.
- DO YOU HAVE THE KIDS?
- HARRISON'S
WITH BILL AND MAURA,
AND...ASTOR AND CODY
ARE...WITH YOU?
- SHIT.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- DID YOU DROP THEM OFF
AT SCHOOL THIS MORNING?
- YEAH, THEY WERE
SEEING THE COUNSELOR FIRST,
AND THEN THEY WERE GOING
TO THEIR REGULAR CLASSES.
- WELL, I JUST WENT
TO GO PICK THEM UP,
AND THE WOMAN IN THE OFFICE SAID
THAT THEY NEVER WENT TO CLASS.
SO I CALLED THE APARTMENT,
AND THERE'S NO ANSWER.
- WELL, WHERE ARE THEY?
- THAT'S MY QUESTION,
BIG BROTHER.
WHERE WOULD THEY GO?
- SAME PLACE ASTOR
KEEPS SAYING SHE WANTS TO GO.
[bird cawing]
ASTOR.
CODY.
HEY.
HOW'D YOU GUYS GET HERE?
- WE WALKED.
DON'T BE MAD, DEXTER.
- THEY WANTED
TO SEE WHERE IT HAPPENED.
WHERE THEY LOST THEIR MOTHER.
I'M NOT MAD.
ASTOR, I'M SORRY.
I SHOULD HAVE
LISTENED TO YOU.
I SHOULD HAVE BROUGHT
YOU BACK HERE LIKE YOU ASKED.
IF YOU WANT TO MOVE BACK HERE,
THEN WE WILL.
WE'LL FIND A WAY
TO MAKE IT WORK.
- NO, WE WON'T.
- ASTOR, I'M SORRY.
- YOU KEEP SAYING THAT,
BUT I DON'T CARE.
YOU RUINED EVERYTHING.
WE'D GOTTEN USED TO IT.
IT WASN'T THAT BAD!
- USED TO WHAT?
- TO THE WAY THINGS WERE!
BEFORE YOU!
WITHOUT A DAD!
- OH.
- AND THEN YOU COME ALONG
AND BECOME
A PART OF THE FAMILY,
AND WE THOUGHT THAT EVERYTHING
WAS GONNA BE GOOD FOREVER.
YOU MADE US THINK THAT!
AND IT'S NOT TRUE.
THINGS GOT WORSE.
AND NOW EVERY TIME
I LOOK AT YOU, I GET SO ANGRY,
BECAUSE IT WAS
ALL JUST A LIE.
- [crying]
IT'S NOT DEXTER'S FAULT.
- [sighs]
I THOUGHT COMING HERE
WOULD HELP.
BUT THAT WAS STUPID.
- NO, I UNDERSTAND.
- IT LOOKS EXACTLY
THE SAME AS BEFORE.
- IT DOES.
- YOU CAN'T EVEN
TELL WHAT HAPPENED.
BUT I KNOW MY MOM DIED THERE.
AND THINGS WILL NEVER
BE THE SAME.
- [crying]
I MISS HER SO MUCH.
- I DO TOO.
- WE ALL DO.
- I DON'T WANT
TO LIVE WITH YOU.
[crying] I WANT TO LIVE
WITH GRANDMA AND GRANDPA.
I WANT TO GO BACK
WITH THEM TONIGHT.
RIGHT NOW!
- HEY.
I'M, UH, HEADING OUT.
YOU WANT TO GRAB
A BITE SOMEWHERE?
- NO, WHY WOULD I
WANNA DO THAT?
- ALL RIGHT.
[bell dings]
- HEY, LIEUTENANT.
DEB TOLD ME ABOUT
THE KYLE BUTLER SKETCHES.
- YEAH, WELL, I'M NOT SURE
HOW USEFUL THEY'LL BE.
THE MOTHER AND TWO CHILDREN
ALL GAVE VERY DIFFERENT
VERSIONS.
- HUH.
- IT'S THEIR BIGGEST LEAD.
SEEMS TO BE GOING NOWHERE.
- DO YOU MIND IF I KEEP
A COPY OF THESE?
- NO, I GOT PLENTY.
[ding]
- ANGEL.
- LET ME ASK YOU A QUESTION.
CAN YOU TELL ME
WHY YOU KEPT THIS MUCH MONEY
A SECRET FROM ME?
- [scoffs]
IT WAS NEVER A SECRET.
THAT'S MY RETIREMENT FUND.
- WELL, NOW
THAT WE'RE MARRIED,
AREN'T WE SUPPOSED
TO SHARE EVERYTHING?
- I DON'T THINK
WE EVER DISCUSSED THAT.
- THEN MAYBE
WE HAVE DIFFERENT IDEAS
ABOUT WHAT A MARRIAGE
SHOULD BE.
BECAUSE I ALWAYS PICTURED
YOU AND I AT 80 YEARS OLD,
WALKING DOWN THE BEACH,
HAND IN HAND.
- I LIKE TO PICTURE THAT
AS WELL, ANGEL.
I LOVE YOU.
BUT I THINK MAYBE
I HAVE MORE OF A...
PRACTICAL SIDE THAN YOU DO.
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- I MEAN I'VE WORKED
MY ENTIRE CAREER
TO SAVE UP,
TO PROTECT MYSELF,
AND YOU LIVE EVERY DAY
LIKE IT'S A PARTY.
IT'S ONE OF THE THINGS
I LIKE ABOUT YOU,
BUT IT ALSO MEANS
THAT YOU SPEND MONEY
FASTER THAN
YOU EVEN MAKE IT.
- OKAY!
- AND IT'S, I'M--
- OKAY, I GET IT.
- I DON'T MEAN TO HURT
YOUR FEELINGS.
- NO, I'M FINE.
I'M IRRESPONSIBLE.
- OH, MARIA.
- EVERYONE KNOWS THAT.
- [sighs]
- HEY, EVERYONE!
DRINKS ON ME.
TONIGHT.
- YEAH! ANGEL!
- [whistling]
- THAT'S WHAT I'M
TALKIN' 'BOUT.
- ANGEL.
- HEY.
SO EVERYONE'S HOME SAFE?
- YEAH, THEY'RE ALL INSIDE.
- YOU THINK THEY'RE FINALLY
SETTLING IN?
- [scoffs]
THEY'RE PACKING.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- ASTOR AND CODY ARE...
LEAVING.
SOON AS THEIR GRANDPARENTS
GET HERE,
THEY'RE GOING BACK TO ORLANDO
WITH THEM.
- DEX, I'M SO SORRY.
FOR HOW LONG?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- WELL, MAYBE
IF I TALK TO ASTOR--
- I ALREADY TRIED.
- AND CODY WANTS TO GO TOO?
- NO, HE WANTS TO STAY.
IT GOT...VERY UPSETTING.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- I REMINDED HIM THAT YOU AND I
ARE BROTHER AND SISTER,
JUST LIKE HIM AND ASTOR,
AND THAT IT'S...
IMPORTANT THAT THEY
NEVER SPLIT UP.
- ALL THE SHIT
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH.
[laughs nervously]
I NEVER WOULD HAVE
MADE IT THROUGH WITHOUT YOU.
- THAT'S WHAT I TRIED
TO TELL HIM.
- DID IT HELP?
- NOT REALLY.
I REALLY WAS TRYING...
TO MAKE IT WORK.
IN MY OWN WAY.
- YEAH, I KNOW YOU WERE.
- [sighs]
I GUESS IT'S TIME
TO FACE REALITY.
- REALITY.
[cell phone vibrating]
- QUINN.
- OKAY, WE HAD SEX.
- [chuckles]
WAS IT GOOD SEX?
- I'VE SAID ALL I'M GONNA SAY.
- ARE WE GONNA HAVE MORE SEX?
- GOOD-BYE.
- COME ON.
HELP ME OUT HERE.
- I'M HANGING UP NOW.
[beep]
[chatter and music]
- SHE WANTS TO LIVE HER LIFE
STASHING AWAY
ALL HER LITTLE PENNIES,
THAT'S--THAT'S HER PROBLEM.
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING
ABOUT THAT.
YOU KNOW?
YOU WANT ANOTHER DRINK?
- YOU BUYING, RIGHT?
- BARTENDER, A CUERVO SILVER.
YOU KNOW HOW MUCH
MONEY SHE'S GOT? IT'S SICK.
DID SHE TELL ME?
CHEERS.
- ANGEL.
IT TRUE YOU MARRIED
MARIA LAGUERTA?
- I DID INDEED.
- [laughs]
CABRON!
YOU GOT YOURSELF
A LITTLE SUGAR MAMA.
- WHAT?
- OH, YEAH.
I REMEMBER WHEN SHE WAS
FIRST STARTING OUT.
SUCH A FINE PIECE OF ASS.
- I THINK YOU NEED TO GET
THE HELL OUT OF HERE.
- [laughs]
[speaking Spanish]
- YOU FUCK!
[laughing]
UHH!
- UHH!
- AAH!
[music growing louder]
* *
[crickets chirping]
- IF THEY NEED ANYTHING,
JUST LET ME KNOW; I'LL SEND IT.
- WE WILL.
THANK YOU.
- I LOST MY INNOCENCE
AT SUCH AN EARLY AGE,
AND IT LEFT
A VERY DAMAGING MARK.
- [crying softly]
CAN'T I STAY
WITH YOU, DEXTER?
- FOR NOW, YOU NEED
TO GO WITH YOUR GRANDPARENTS.
DON'T WORRY, WE'LL STILL
SEE EACH OTHER ALL THE TIME.
ORLANDO'S NOT SO FAR.
- [sniffles]
YES, IT IS.
- ANY SHRINK COULD TELL YOU
THAT'S WHY I'VE ALWAYS
LIKED CHILDREN.
BECAUSE THEY CONNECT ME
TO WHAT I CAN NEVER GET BACK.
- I DON'T WANT TO GO, DEXTER.
- I DON'T WANT YOU TO GO.
ASTOR...
- WHAT?
- YOUR MOTHER LOVED YOU MORE
THAN YOU COULD EVER IMAGINE.
AND I...
ME TOO.
[engine starts]
CODY AND ASTOR SHOWED ME
THAT I CAN STILL CARE
ABOUT SOMETHING.
THAT MAKES LETTING THEM GO
ALL THAT MUCH HARDER.
AND IT'S LOSING THEM
THAT MAKES ME REALIZE
THERE MUST BE SOME SMALL PART
OF THAT INNOCENT CHILD
STILL INSIDE ME.
[scissors snip]
BECAUSE, JUST LIKE ASTOR,
I WAS FOOLISH ENOUGH
TO THINK THAT THINGS
WOULD ALWAYS BE GOOD.
BUT THEY'RE NOT.
THEY'RE WORSE.
[sizzling]
MUCH WORSE.
NORMALLY, HAVING A TARGET
WOULD MAKE ME FEEL GOOD,
GIVE ME DIRECTION,
A SENSE OF PURPOSE.
BUT NOW...
IT MEANS NOTHING.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
GOING TO MAKE ME FEEL BETTER.
- SHOULD WE GO HOME?
- GIVE ME A MINUTE.