- PREVIOUSLY ON DEXTER...
- I THINK I MAY HAVE A LEAD
ON KYLE BUTLER.
- I DIDN'T KNOW YOU PEOPLE
WERE WORKING THIS.
THE MITCHELLS ARE
IN A SAFE HOUSE.
- I JUST WANT TO SHOW THEM
A PHOTO.
- THERE IS A GREAT, BIG,
SHIT-UGLY WORLD
OUT THERE, JONAH.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT ME
TO DO?
- OKAY, WE HAD SEX.
- WAS IT GOOD SEX?
- I'VE SAID ALL
I'M GONNA SAY.
- LOPEZ COLLAPSED
WHILE ON DUTY TODAY.
HE'S BEEN HOSPITALIZED
WITH INTERNAL BLEEDING.
BATISTA COULD NOT ONLY
LOSE HIS JOB,
HE COULD SERVE TIME.
- I KNOW WHO PURCHASED
THE SANTA MUERTE ICONS.
- WHAT'D YOU GET?
- TWO GUYS IN THEIR 30s.
STRONG ACCENTS, POSSIBLY
RECENT IMMIGRANTS
FROM VENEZUELA.
THEY DID THIS TO HIM BECAUSE
HE STARTED TALKING TO ME.
- BOYD FOWLER, DIVISION
OF DEAD ANIMAL PICKUP.
HOBBIES--STORING WOMEN
IN FORMALDEHYDE.
- WE'LL DO A SHIFT TOGETHER.
TOMORROW MORNING,
8:00 SHARP.
- AN OLD TOURIST
WELCOME CENTER.
TOTALLY ISOLATED.
OH, I WISH YOU COULD SEE
THE ROOM I SET UP FOR YOU.
ALL THE WOMEN YOU'VE KILLED.
- YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE GETTING INTO.
- [panting]
- DON'T--
SHE SAW EVERYTHING.
SHE SAW...ME.
[quirky music]
* *
- I'M NOT LIKING
THE TREND HERE.
YOU RIP A MAN APART
IN A PUBLIC BATHROOM...
- NO ONE SAW.
- YOU NEARLY BOTCH
BOYD'S KILL.
- HE'S DEAD, ISN'T HE?
- YEAH.
AND NOW YOU'VE GOT HER.
WHAT'S THE FIRST RULE
OF THE CODE?
- NEVER KILL AN INNOCENT.
- DON'T GET CAUGHT.
SO WHAT'S YOUR PLAN HERE?
NURSE HER BACK TO HEALTH
SO SHE CAN GO TO THE POLICE?
SHE GIVES THE COPS ENOUGH
TO TRACK YOU DOWN,
THEN EVERYTHING
FALLS APART.
HARRISON GROWS UP
VISITING YOU ON DEATH ROW.
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
- BECAUSE SHE'S DYING.
- AND YOU'RE A SERIAL KILLER.
I'D THINK YOU COULD
HANDLE THAT.
YOU DIDN'T DO THIS
TO HER, DEX.
SHE'S NOT
YOUR RESPONSIBILITY.
GO HOME AND TAKE CARE OF
YOUR SON.
- [sound slowed]
IT'S OKAY. DON'T MOVE.
EVERYTHING WILL BE OKAY.
- [groaning]
- DON'T! IT'S OKAY.
IT'S OKAY!
CALM DOWN.
STOP FIGHTING ME.
- [screaming]
- I'M NOT HERE TO HURT YOU.
STOP!
- [gasping and groaning
hysterically]
[gasps and groans cease]
- FUCK! FUCK! FUCK!
[cell phone ringing]
WHAT?
- JESUS.
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
- SORRY. IT'S THE MIDDLE
OF THE NIGHT.
- IN CALIFORNIA, MAYBE.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- NOTHING.
I'M JUST...TIRED.
- YOU ARE?
I JUST PULLED AN ALL-NIGHTER
AT A CRIME SCENE.
TOTALLY FRIED
AND I'VE GOT JACK SHIT.
- SO THE BABYSITTER'S
BEEN THERE ALL NIGHT?
- MASUKA'S TRYING.
HE REALLY IS.
BUT THE BLOOD JUST
DOESN'T TALK TO HIM
THE WAY IT DOES
TO YOU.
I REALLY NEED YOUR HELP
ON THIS.
- IT'S NOT A GOOD TIME.
I'VE GOT HARRISON.
- WELL, WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE BABYSITTER?
- PROBABLY GETTING READY
TO KILL ME.
- LOOK, I KNOW YOU'RE STILL
ON LEAVE,
AND YOU KNOW I WOULDN'T ASK
IF IT WEREN'T IMPORTANT.
DON'T MAKE ME BEG.
- DEB, LOOK, IT'S--
[sighs]
MAYBE I CAN USE THE CRIME SCENE
TO GET AN I.D.
ON SLEEPING BEAUTY HERE.
OKAY, I'LL DO IT.
- YOU WILL?
- YEAH. OF COURSE.
YOU'RE MY SISTER.
WHERE, UH--
WHERE SHOULD I GO?
- 1132 MOREDO.
IT'S A BOTANICA.
JUST FOLLOW THE FUCKING
NEWS VANS.
YOU'RE THE BEST,
YOU KNOW THAT?
[beep]
HELLO?
[overlapping conversations]
- DEX, OVER HERE.
YOU'RE JUST IN TIME.
THE CORONER'S CHOMPING
AT THE BIT TO REMOVE THE BODY.
- IT'S A BIT OF A CIRCUS.
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
IT'S BARNUM AND BAILEY.
- [yelling in Spanish]
- YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
WE'RE WORKING ON IT!
- WHAT'S HE SAYING?
- I HAVE NO IDEA.
BUT THE GENERAL COMPLAINT IS
THERE ARE FEWER BEHEADINGS
IN THE RICH PARTS
OF MIAMI.
- BEHEADINGS?
- YEAH. AND THAT'S NOT EVEN
THE FUCKED UP PART.
- DEXTROUS.
- VINCE.
WHOA, YOU WEREN'T KIDDING
ABOUT THE FUCKED UP PART.
- IT'S A POTENTIAL WITNESS.
AND IT'S THE SECOND THIS WEEK.
- SO WHAT YOU GOT?
- UH, WE'RE THINKING,
UH, MACHETE.
- OKAY. WHAT ELSE?
- JUST MACHETE.
WE'VE BEEN UP ALL NIGHT.
WE'RE TOO TIRED TO THINK.
THAT'S WHY I CALLED YOU.
SO?
- SO THE BEHEADING OBVIOUSLY
WENT DOWN HERE.
HE WAS STANDING.
WHACK ONE,
AND THE VICTIM GOES DOWN.
WHACK TWO...
WHACK THREE...
AND CERVICAL VERTEBRAE
ARE PRETTY MUCH TOAST.
SEPARATION COMPLETE.
WE HAVE LIFTOFF.
- THAT'S WHAT I'VE BEEN SAYING.
- NOT REALLY.
LET HIM WORK.
- EYES AND TONGUE
REMOVED HERE.
- THAT TONGUE'S IN
THE ICE CHEST.
DO YOU WANT TO SEE IT?
- NO, NOT REALLY.
HAS ANYONE BEEN SMOKING
IN HERE?
- IT'S 2010. WHO SMOKES?
- UH, MACHETE MAN,
I THINK.
A SMALL CIGAR.
HIGHLY UNSTABLE ASH.
SHORT, TORN TOBACCO LEAVES.
IT'S A CHEAP ONE.
LIKE A TIPARILLO.
[sighs]
I'D LOOK FOR THAT.
- SO MACHETE AND TIPARILLO.
DEFINITELY STYLIN'.
- FUCK ME IN BOTH EARS.
OKAY, PEOPLE, OUR KILLERS LEFT
THROUGH THAT DOOR
INTO THE ALLEY.
SO LET'S SWEEP IT
FOR SMALL CIGAR BUTTS.
- HEY, WATCH YOUR STEP,
FELLAS.
WATCH THE EV.
WATCH THE EV!
THANK YOU.
WATCH THE EV.
SO...THAT, UH,
CIGAR ASH STUFF...
- YEAH?
- YOU LEARN THAT IN GRAD SCHOOL?
- UH, HAVANA ROOM.
- HAVANA ROOM.
[chuckles]
OH, GOOD TO HAVE YOU BACK.
YOU KNOW,
IN A SUPPORTING ROLE.
ASSISTING...ME.
- YEAH. THANKS.
I GOTTA GO.
- DON'T YOU WANT TO SEE
IF WE FIND THE CIGAR?
- I JUST WANT TO FIND OUT
WHO THAT GIRL IS
BEFORE THE M-99
WEARS OFF.
ABSOLUTELY.
I'LL DROP BY THE STATION
LATER.
- OH...HE'S UP.
- HE'S BEEN UP FOR HOURS.
- I KNOW.
I MISSED YOU TOO.
I'M SO SORRY.
I KNOW I'M LATE.
- LATE DOESN'T QUITE
CAPTURE IT.
IT'S BEEN ALL NIGHT.
- I KNOW, IT'S JUST...
I KILLED A MAN
IN FRONT OF A WITNESS
I JUST HAD TO TRANQUILIZE
TO KEEP HER
FROM SCRATCHING MY EYES OUT.
- WHAT?
- I'LL MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
- [scoffs]
I DON'T THINK SO.
- WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
- IT MEANS I DON'T THINK
THIS IS A GOOD FIT,
AND I WON'T BE RETURNING.
- IT IS.
IT IS A GOOD FIT.
HARRISON LIKES YOU.
- AND I REALLY LIKE HIM.
WHICH IS WHAT PAINS ME
SO MUCH ABOUT THIS, BUT...
HE NEEDS A RELIABLE PARENT.
ESPECIALLY WITH HIS MOTHER
GONE.
- I'M RELIABLE.
- WELL, I GUESS WE USE
DIFFERENT DICTIONARIES.
- IT WILL NEVER HAPPEN AGAIN.
- DO YOU THINK?
MY MOTHER TOLD ME
WHEN I WAS JUST A LITTLE GIRL,
"NEVER LIE TO SOMEONE
WHO TRUSTS YOU.
NEVER TRUST SOMEONE
WHO LIES TO YOU."
IT'S A SHAME, REALLY.
WE GOT OFF
TO SUCH A GOOD START.
- I MISS YOUR MOM.
[Latin music]
* *
- I UNDERSTAND THAT,
BUT THE BUREAU SAID NO.
- EVEN THOUGH THE ONLY CLUE
YOU HAVE IN THE TRINITY CASE
IS KYLE BUTLER,
AND I MIGHT KNOW WHO THAT IS.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- ASK AGAIN, RAY.
- THERE'S NO POINT.
- I THOUGHT YOU HAD CLOUT.
- NOT WHEN IT COMES
TO DOING AN END RUN
ON SAFE HOUSE PROCEDURES.
LOOK, OFFER STILL STANDS.
GIVE ME THE PHOTO,
I'LL SHOW IT TO THE FAMILY.
- I TOLD YOU,
I CAN'T DO THAT.
IT'S A SENSITIVE SITUATION.
- IT'S YOUR CALL.
- GREAT. THANKS.
[beep]
HERE WE GO.
[starts engine]
THERE'S THE SAFE HOUSE,
AND THERE'S JONAH MITCHELL.
- OKAY, WE MAY HAVE FINALLY
CAUGHT A BREAK
IN THE SANTA MUERTE CASE,
SO LISTEN UP, PEOPLE.
DETECTIVE MORGAN.
- OKAY, IT'S TOO SOON
TO CELEBRATE,
AND MOST OF US ARE
TOO FUCKING TIRED ANYWAY,
BUT WE FOUND THIS
JUST OUTSIDE THE BACK ENTRANCE
OF THE BOTANICA
WHERE FAUZI WAS MURDERED.
- IS THAT A CIGAR BUTT?
- VERY PERCEPTIVE,
DETECTIVE QUINN.
AND MAY I THANK YOU FOR
GETTING YOUR LAZY ASS
OFF THE COUCH AND JOINING US--
SO THANK YOU.
IT'S A TIPARILLO BUTT,
AND WE HAVE REASON TO BELIEVE
IT WAS HANDLED
BY ONE OF THE TWO
ASSAILANTS.
- SO WHAT ARE WE TALKING ABOUT,
DNA SWAB?
- EVEN BETTER.
- OH, THERE'S A 3/4 PARTIAL
THUMBPRINT ON THE SIDE,
AND IT HAS TO BE PROCESSED
MANUALLY--IT'S INCOMPLETE.
BUT WE EXPECT TO HEAR BACK
WITHIN A DAY.
- AND THERE'S THE MAN
WE HAVE TO THANK FOR IT--
MY NEPHEW HARRISON.
HE LENT US HIS DAD.
- LOOK AT THOSE CHEEKS!
MAY I?
- SURE.
- [fawning in Spanish]
- [speaking Spanish]
- YOU LOOK LIKE YOUR MOMMY.
- OH, AND HE'S GOT
DADDY'S EYES.
- AND YOUR PENIS SIZE.
- NO, IT'S BIGGER.
IT'S MUCH BIGGER.
[laughter]
- WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT?
BETTER THAN DOUGHNUTS.
- THIS YOUR IDEA
OF QUALITY TIME,
USING YOUR SON AS COVER?
- HE'S ENJOYING IT.
THEY'RE ENJOYING IT.
IT'S A WIN-WIN.
BESIDES,
IT'S FOR A GOOD CAUSE.
I NEED TO FIND OUT
WHO THIS GIRL IS
BEFORE SHE WAKES UP,
WHICH WILL BE SOON.
AH, DAMN IT.
COME ON, COME ON...
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING NOW,
STEALING FROM A CO-WORKER?
- BORROWING.
- YOU REALLY THING
VINCE MASUKA WON'T NOTICE
HALF HIS MEDICINE CABINET
IS MISSING?
- I DON'T CARE.
HE'S A HYPOCHONDRIAC.
SHE ACTUALLY NEEDS THIS STUFF.
[blip]
LUMEN ANN PIERCE,
FROM MINNESOTA.
NO WARRANTS.
NOT EVEN A TRAFFIC VIOLATION.
- YEAH, AND NO MISSING PERSONS
REPORT EITHER.
NO ONE'S LOOKING FOR HER.
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING,
I SHOULD JUST LET HER DIE?
- WELL, YOU CAN'T JUST
LET HER GO.
THIS ISN'T SOME FAIRY TALE
WHERE SHE WAKES UP
AND YOU GET TO BE THE HANDSOME
PRINCE WHO SAVED HER.
IF SHE WAKES UP,
SHE'LL CALL THE POLICE.
- YOU THINK I DON'T KNOW THAT?
- HOW YOU DOING?
[tapping keys]
- HEY, ISN'T IT ABOUT TIME
FOR HIS NAP?
- YEAH.
OH, I KNOW THE FEELING.
- YOU DO?
I FLATLINED HOURS AGO.
I'M HEADING HOME
TO TAKE A NAP.
- HEY, WILL YOU DO ME A FAVOR
AND TAKE HIM WITH YOU?
I'VE GOT SOMEONE
EXPECTING ME.
- WHAT ABOUT THE NANNY?
- SHE NEEDED A BREAK.
- AFTER TWO DAYS?
- IT WOULD BE A HUGE HELP.
AND HE'S GONNA GO
RIGHT TO SLEEP.
HE'S WAY OVERDUE
FOR A NAP.
- ALL RIGHT.
IF YOU CARRY HIM TO THE CAR.
HE'S GETTING HEAVY.
- ANGEL.
- WHAT'S THIS?
- AN ADDRESS.
I DIDN'T WANT TO GIVE IT TO YOU
IN FRONT OF EVERYBODY ELSE.
- IT'S A HOSPITAL.
- MM-HMM.
THAT'S WHERE SERGEANT LOPEZ
ENDED UP
AFTER YOUR LITTLE FIGHT.
YOU NEED TO GO APOLOGIZE.
- NO. NO.
- [speaks Spanish]
- NO.
HE'S THE ONE THAT SHOULD
APOLOGIZE TO ME.
- HE'S THE ONE WHO HAS
A BROKEN NOSE,
A BROKEN RIB,
AND A PUNCTURED LUNG.
ANGEL, POR FAVOR.
- I SHOULD HAVE
BROKEN HIS JAW
FOR WHAT HE SAID ABOUT YOU.
- I'M NOT GONNA ARGUE
WITH YOU.
INTERNAL AFFAIRS
IS COMING BY TOMORROW,
AND THEY NEED TO KNOW
THAT IT'S OVER.
THAT THERE'S NO BAD BLOOD
BETWEEN YOU, OKAY?
I'M NOT ASKING.
- SORRY IF I SCARED YOU
BEFORE.
MAYBE WE CAN START AGAIN?
YOU PROBABLY HAVE A HEADACHE.
THE SEDATIVE DOES THAT.
I GOT YOU ASPIRIN FOR IT.
ALSO ANTIBIOTICS.
YOU HAVE A PRETTY
SERIOUS FEVER.
THEY'LL HELP
BRING THAT DOWN.
I'M NOT TRYING TO DRUG YOU.
THEY REALLY ARE JUST
ANTIBIOTICS.
SEE?
YOU'RE DEHYDRATED.
CAN YOU DRINK?
CAREFUL, CAREFUL, CAREFUL.
I'M NOT GONNA HURT YOU.
- WHERE AM I?
- A SAFE PLACE.
FAR FROM BOYD.
- I'M...
NOT TAKING ANYTHING.
- WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
LOOK, YOU REALLY NEED
TO TALK TO ME.
- RACHEL.
- OKAY.
RACHEL...
I'M NOT GONNA HURT YOU.
I JUST WANT TO SEE YOU
GET BETTER.
- WHY DIDN'T YOU TAKE ME
TO THE HOSPITAL?
- YOU KNOW WHY.
- NO, I DON'T.
- BECAUSE YOU SAW ME...
IN THE HOUSE.
- I DIDN'T SEE ANYTHING.
- WE BOTH KNOW
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
- I WOULD NEVER TELL
ANYONE.
PLEASE...
LET ME GO.
- I CAN'T.
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
WITH ME?
- NOTHING.
- ARE YOU...GONNA SELL ME?
- SELL YOU? NO.
- THEN WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO?
- NOTHING.
I'M NOT GONNA DO ANYTHING.
I'M NOT LYING.
LOOK, YOU CAN'T EVEN
THINK STRAIGHT
WITH A FEVER LIKE THAT.
YOU NEED TO TAKE THESE.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
- NO, STAY AWAY FROM ME!
STAY AWAY FROM ME!
- I'M TRYING TO HELP YOU.
- LET ME OUT! LET ME OUT!
- I CAN'T DO THAT.
- NO, PLEASE, LET ME GO.
I CAN'T--I CAN'T--
I CAN'T GO THROUGH IT AGAIN!
JUST KILL ME NOW.
PLEASE!
[sobbing]
- HARRY'S RIGHT.
I NEED A PLAN.
[knocks on door]
- HOW YOU DOING, LOPEZ?
- HOW'S IT LOOK LIKE
I'M DOING?
- LISTEN, THE OTHER NIGHT,
WE BOTH HAD A LITTLE
TOO MUCH TO DRINK.
AND, UM...
WHEN YOU INSULTED MY WIFE,
I JUST SAW RED.
I'M SORRY.
I'M NOT THE FIRST GUY
TO TAKE A SWING AT YOU.
ARE YOU REALLY GONNA
BUST MY CHOPS
WITH I.A. OVER THIS?
YOU KNOW THAT LINE
BETWEEN A FEW
AND A FEW TOO MANY?
- ALL TOO WELL.
- YEAH, WELL, I HAD
WAY TOO MANY THAT NIGHT.
AND I SHOULD HAVE
HELD MY TEMPER, BUT I DIDN'T.
AND I APOLOGIZE.
LO SIENTO.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT ELSE
TO SAY.
SO ARE WE OKAY OR WHAT?
- YOU'RE OKAY.
I'M IN A FUCKING HOSPITAL.
NO...WE'RE OKAY.
I'M NOT GONNA PRESS CHARGES,
BATISTA.
NOW GET THE FUCK OUT
OF MY ROOM.
[keyboard keys tapping]
- THE BABYSITTER
DOESN'T TRUST ME
BECAUSE OF THE LIES.
LUMEN DOESN'T TRUST ME
BECAUSE OF THE TRUTH.
[beep]
THERE MUST BE A NAME
FOR THAT.
OH, RIGHT, DEXTER MORGAN...
THE PROBLEM IS LUMEN KNOWS
WAY TOO MUCH ABOUT ME,
AND I KNOW NOTHING
ABOUT HER.
HMM, AN UNPAID MOTEL BILL.
I WAS HOPING FOR MORE,
BUT AT LEAST
IT'S A PLACE TO START.
HEY, HOW WAS YOUR NAP?
- WHAT NAP?
HE WOKE UP THE SECOND
WE GOT BACK.
- OH. SORRY.
FIX YOU SOMETHING TO EAT?
- I'M TOO TIRED TO CHEW.
[toy piano notes play]
DAMN IT, DEXTER!
- WHAT? WHAT IS IT?
- NOTHING. IT'S JUST--
[notes play]
WHAT IS THIS?
- IT'S A LITTLE
TOY KEYBOARD.
- NO, I MEAN,
WHY AM I SITTING ON IT?
WHY ARE WE LIVING
LIKE THIS?
BETWEEN THE BABY STUFF
AND YOUR STUFF AND MY STUFF,
WHICH I CAN BARELY SEE
ANYMORE,
I FEEL LIKE A FUCKING
REFUGEE.
[baby fussing]
- I GET IT. I GET IT.
OKAY...
[sighs]
YOU NEED SOME PEACE
AND QUIET.
WE'LL HEAD OUT
FOR A WHILE.
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
[scoffs]
- SO WHAT CAN I DO
FOR YOU?
- UH, I'M NOT SURE.
I THINK MY WIFE--
UH, HIS MOM--
MIGHT HAVE LEFT
HER LUGGAGE HERE.
LUMEN PIERCE.
- LET'S HAVE A LOOK-SEE.
CAN YOU SPELL THAT, PLEASE?
- YEAH, IT'S P-I-E-R-C-E.
- THE OTHER NAME.
THE WEIRD ONE. NO OFFENSE.
- UH, LUMEN.
L-U-M-E-N.
[computer beeps]
- MM-HMM.
I REMEMBER HER.
YOUR WIFE PREPAID TWO WEEKS.
IT'S BEEN OVER A MONTH.
- YEAH, CHANGE OF PLANS.
WE ENDED UP STAYING WITH FRIENDS
IN NORTH BEACH.
- WELL, SHE NEVER
CHECKED OUT.
WE, UH, SENT HER FILE
TO A COLLECTION AGENCY.
- OH, GEE, IT'D BE
A LOT SIMPLER
IF YOU'D JUST LET ME
TAKE CARE OF IT.
OH, DO YOU, BY ANY CHANCE,
STILL HAVE HER LUGGAGE?
- YEAH, IN STORAGE.
- I'D APPRECIATE IT.
WE BOTH WOULD.
- $320 AND WE'RE SQUARE.
- OKAY.
- PUT YOUR JOHN HANCOCK HERE,
AND I'LL GO FETCH
YOUR WIFE'S LUGGAGE.
- GREAT.
TEN MONTHS OLD AND YOU'VE HAD
YOUR FIRST CIGARETTE.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
"DEAR LUMEN,
"I KNOW IT FEELS LIKE
THE END OF THE WORLD RIGHT NOW,
"BUT IT'S NOT.
"I UNDERSTAND WHY YOU FELT
YOU HAD TO LEAVE.
"AND BELIEVE ME, YOU HAVE
NOTHING TO BE ASHAMED OF.
"AND AS FOR YOUR FATHER,
"I KNOW HE SAID THINGS
HE REGRETS,
"EVEN THOUGH
HE'LL NEVER ADMIT IT.
"WE MISS YOU.
WE LOVE YOU.
"TAKE ALL THE TIME
YOU NEED,
"BUT THEN PLEASE COME HOME.
"IT'S NOT A FAMILY
WITHOUT YOU.
LOVE, MOM."
- [crying]
- DEXTER.
- [whispering]
OH, SORRY.
I WOKE YOU UP.
I WAS TRYING TO BE QUIET.
- YOU WERE GONE A LONG TIME.
I WAS WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
- JUST WENT FOR
A LITTLE DRIVE.
- SORRY ABOUT BEFORE.
AND IN CASE
YOU DIDN'T KNOW,
YOU AND HARRISON ARE
THE MOST IMPORTANT PEOPLE TO ME.
YOU'RE THE ONLY
IMPORTANT PEOPLE.
YOU GUYS CAN
STAY HERE FOREVER.
I DON'T CARE ABOUT
THE MESS.
I'M THE FUCKING SLOB
IN THE FAMILY ANYWAY.
- [chuckles]
YOU WANT A BEER?
- YEAH.
I WOULD LOVE A BEER.
[rings doorbell]
- MR. MORGAN.
- PLEASE GIVE US
ANOTHER CHANCE.
- I DON'T THINK
IT'S A GOOD IDEA.
- I KNOW I SCREWED UP.
- [sighs]
THERE'S NO NEED TO APOLOGIZE.
HARRISON IS A WONDERFUL CHILD,
AND YOU WILL HAVE NO TROUBLE
FINDING SOMEONE ELSE
TO WATCH HIM.
- I DON'T WANT SOMEONE ELSE
- WELL, I'M FLATTERED--
- AND I HEARD YOU.
ABOUT HOW YOU NEED
TO BE ABLE TO TRUST ME.
- WHAT I SAID WAS
I DON'T TRUST YOU.
[Harrison fussing]
- [sighs]
LOOK, THERE WAS
AN EMERGENCY.
A GIRL WAS BADLY HURT.
SHE WAS VERY NEAR DEATH.
I SPENT THE NIGHT TRYING
TO HELP HER,
AND THEN I WAS CALLED
TO A CRIME SCENE BY MY SISTER.
THAT'S...WHERE I WAS.
REALLY.
AND I'M HERE NOW BECAUSE
WE INTERVIEWED 30 PEOPLE,
AND YOU'RE THE ONE...
WHO DIDN'T SCARE ME,
BASICALLY.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
I COULD TRUST HARRISON TO.
- [chuckles]
WELL, YOU ARE HOLDING HIM
A LITTLE BIT LIKE A FOOTBALL.
OH...
WHAT DO THEY CALL IT?
A LEAP OF FAITH.
I GUESS IT'S ONE
ON BOTH OUR PARTS.
ONE MORE CHANCE, MR. MORGAN,
BUT THAT'S IT.
- LOOK AT THIS.
- LOOK AT WHAT?
- NOTICE ANYTHING MISSING?
- HOW WOULD I KNOW?
- SOMEBODY'S BEEN DIPPING
INTO MY MEDS,
AND METHINKS ME KNOWS WHO.
- YEAH, UH, DEXTER WAS
BACK HERE ALONE YESTERDAY.
I DON'T KNOW,
MAYBE IT WAS HIM.
- NO MOTIVE, DETECTIVE.
YOU, ON THE OTHER HAND,
HAVE BEEN GETTING DOWN AND DIRTY
WITH THE HOTTEST POTTY MOUTH
IN THE SOUTH.
NOW, I APPRECIATE YOU TAKING
PREVENTATIVE MEASURES
SO AS NOT TO PASS ON
WHATEVER SICK SCURVY
YOU MAY CARRY ON TO HER.
- MM.
- I'M WILLING TO SHARE.
[whispering]
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS ASK.
- OKAY, I DIDN'T TAKE
YOUR MEDS.
AND I'M NOT GETTING
DOWN AND DIRTY WITH DEBRA.
OKAY?
- MAY I JUST SAY THAT
I ADMIRE YOUR CHIVALRY?
IT'S A RARE MAN
WHO WON'T KISS AND TELL.
- MAKE SURE YOU GET
THE NAMES AND NUMBERS...
[elevator dings]
GET BACK TO ME
WHEN YOU FINISH.
- MM-HMM.
- EXCUSE ME.
MCCOURT...
JUST WANTED TO LET YOU KNOW
THAT I PAID SERGEANT LOPEZ
A VISIT YESTERDAY.
- SO I HEARD.
- I APOLOGIZED, HE ACCEPTED.
WE'RE JAKE.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
- HEY, YOU PUT A COP
IN THE HOSPITAL.
WHAT HAPPENS NOW
IS UP TO THE DEPARTMENT,
NOT HIM.
- MEANING WHAT?
- FACT IS,
IT'S ASSAULT AND BATTERY
AGAINST A FELLOW OFFICER.
- IT'S A FEW PUNCHES AGAINST
A DRUNKEN LOUDMOUTH.
- GOOD MORNING, JIM.
- LIEUTENANT.
- YOU MEAN TO TELL ME
YOU HAVE NOTHING
MORE IMPORTANT TO DO
THAN TO INVESTIGATE
A BAR FIGHT?
- HOW'S THE TIMELINE COMING
ON THE SANTA MUERTE CASE?
- THE TIMELINE'S JUST FINE.
- I'M DUE UPSTAIRS
IN 20 MINUTES,
SO WE SHOULD GET GOING.
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME COFFEE?
- THAT WOULD BE WONDERFUL.
- MY HUSBAND'S NOT WRONG,
YOU KNOW.
- HOW'S THAT?
- WELL, CONSIDERING THE FACT
THAT THE OTHER OFFICER
INVOLVED--
- THE ASSAULT VICTIM.
- IT WAS JUST
A BAR FIGHT, JIM.
NOW, YOU AND I BOTH KNOW
THEY HAPPEN ALL THE TIME.
OKAY, I'M WONDERING
WHAT CAN END THIS.
- SEE, I'M MORE INTERESTED
IN WHAT STARTED IT.
BECAUSE ACCORDING
TO SERGEANT LOPEZ'S DEPOSITION,
HE SAID, DRUNKENLY,
THAT YOU GIVE THE BEST BLOW JOB
IN MIAMI.
- IS THAT PART OF
THE OFFICIAL RECORD?
- SHOULD IT BE?
- [sighs]
- HEY, GOOD NEWS.
MASUKA FOUND A MATCH
ON THAT PARTIAL PRINT
WE HAD FROM THE CIGAR BUTT.
OR ARE YOU NO LONGER INTERESTED
IN SOLVING HOMICIDES?
- HUH?
- CARLOS FUENTES.
YOU'RE GONNA LOVE THIS.
HE'S GOT A BROTHER. MARCO.
THEY LIVE TOGETHER,
AND I GOT THE ADDRESS.
TWO OF THEM.
DOES THAT SOUND LIKE
WHAT WE'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR,
OR DOES THAT SOUND LIKE
WHAT WE'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR?
- I'LL GET A TEAM TOGETHER.
LET'S, UH, GET THESE GUYS.
- AND WHERE'S QUINN AGAIN?
FUCKNOSE IS GONNA MISS
THE PARTY.
- I HAVE NO IDEA.
WHO KNOWS?
[cell phone ringing]
- FUCK.
- HOLD ON. HOLD ON.
HOLD ON, HOLD ON,
HOLD ON.
OKAY, GO.
GO, GO, GO, GO.
MORGAN, YOU, YOU, YOU.
THE OTHER END OF THE HALL.
YOU, UPSTAIRS.
- FREEZE!
- NO, NO, NO.
WE WANT FUENTES.
LET HIM GO. LET HIM GO.
GO!
[Latin music playing]
* *
[knocks on door]
[music stops]
OPEN UP. POLICE.
[baby crying]
- POLICE. POLICIA!
[speaking Spanish]
- NOBODY MOVE.
HOLY SHIT.
- [speaking Spanish]
- WE WANT THESE GUYS.
FUENTES. FUENTES.
FUENTES.
- [speaking Spanish]
- [gasps]
[speaks Spanish]
- NO HABLA.
- [speaks Spanish]
[woman whimpering]
[floor creaking]
- [speaks Spanish]
- YOU CUT HIM AND I'LL BLOW
YOUR FUCKING HEAD OFF.
- [speaks Spanish]
- YOU HEAR ME?
- LET HIM GO.
- [speaks Spanish]
- YOU LET HIM GO!
- EVERYBODY CLEAR?
REPORT IN.
- DIAZ, CLEAR.
- MANSON, CLEAR.
- RESPOND.
- DETECTIVE MORGAN,
YOU CLEAR?
- [speaks Spanish]
- YES, CLEAR.
- YOU STUPID BITCH.
- AAH...HELP.
[gunshots]
- MEDIC!
I NEED A FUCKING MEDIC!
[police radio droning]
DON'T YOU DARE
LET HIM DIE.
- YOU OKAY?
- FINE.
FUCK, I SHOULD HAVE SHOT FUENTES
WHEN I HAD THE CHANCE!
- AND RISK KILLING THAT KID?
- HE MIGHT DIE ANYWAY.
- AND HE MIGHT LIVE,
THANKS TO YOU.
WE NEARLY CAUGHT THOSE FUCKS.
YOU DID GOOD.
- YOU WEREN'T THERE.
- LUMEN ANN PIERCE,
FROM MINNESOTA.
IF I CAN GET THE CROTCHETY
JUDGMENTAL BABYSITTER
FROM IRELAND TO TRUST ME,
I SAY, WHY NOT YOU?
- HYAH!
- UNH!
OUCH.
- AAH!
STOP! STOP! HELP ME!
HELP! HELP ME!
- DO YOU NEED A RIDE?
- YEAH, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
OUT HERE?
HEY, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- MAN, SHE IS FUCKED UP!
[car drives away]
- AAH! NO! NO!
NO! NO!
- LUMEN...
- NO! NO!
- LUMEN. LUMEN
LUMEN, LUMEN...
WOULD YOU STOP?
STOP.
WOULD YOU STOP!
SHH...
- YOU KNOW HOW CLOSE
YOU CAME BACK THERE?
IF SHE'D GOTTEN IN THAT CAR,
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN ALL OVER.
- WHERE ARE WE GOING?
- BELIEVE ME,
SHE WILL NEVER TRUST YOU.
- WHERE ARE YOU TAKING ME?
- FIRST RULE OF THE CODE,
DEXTER,
DON'T GET CAUGHT.
AND YOU'RE OUT
OF OPTIONS NOW.
- LET ME GO.
- SHE'S LEFT YOU NO CHOICE.
- QUIET.
[Latin music playing]
* *
- JONAH?
HEY. DON'T BE AFRAID.
I'M A COP.
MIAMI METRO.
- DO I KNOW YOU?
- [whispering] I THINK I KNOW
WHO KYLE BUTLER IS.
DO YOU RECOGNIZE THIS MAN?
- WHY DO YOU WANT TO KNOW?
- IS THIS KYLE BUTLER?
- HEY, BACK AWAY!
BACK AWAY!
- I'M A COP. IT'S OKAY.
- KEEP YOUR HANDS WHERE
I CAN FUCKIN' SEE 'EM,
AND SHUT THE HELL UP.
JONAH,
GO TO THE CAR NOW.
TURN AROUND.
[handcuffs click shut]
- COME ON. MOVE.
- PLEASE...DON'T!
- JUST MOVE.
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
OH...OH...
- LOOK AT THIS.
- NO! NO, NO.
- LOOK.
[flies buzzing]
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE GIRLS BEFORE YOU.
THIS IS WHAT WAS GONNA
HAPPEN TO YOU.
EVERY ONE OF THESE BARRELS
HAS A BODY IN IT.
BOYD PRESERVED THEM
IN FORMALDEHYDE
SO HE COULD COME
AND VISIT.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
I SAVED YOUR LIFE.
- HOW DO I KNOW THAT
YOU DIDN'T KILL THESE GIRLS?
- YOU DON'T.
IT'S A LEAP OF FAITH...
FOR BOTH OF US.
MY WIFE WAS MURDERED...
BRUTALLY...
BY SOMEONE LIKE BOYD.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE ANY MORE
INNOCENT PEOPLE DIE.
HERE, YOU DON'T BELIEVE ME?
TAKE IT.
- NO.
- TAKE IT. IT'S YOURS.
- OH...
- AAH!
ARE YOU DONE?
[Lumen sobbing]
- I TELL YOU TO LEAVE
TRINITY'S FAMILY ALONE,
AND INSTEAD,
YOU GO BEHIND MY BACK.
AND BASED ON WHAT? THIS?
A CUT-AND-PASTE SKETCH
YOU THINK RESEMBLES
DEXTER MORGAN?
- THE KID RECOGNIZED HIM.
- HE IDENTIFIED DEXTER
AS KYLE BUTLER?
- HE DIDN'T GET A CHANCE,
BUT I COULD TELL.
- OH, YOU COULD TELL.
AND DID JONAH CONVEY THIS I.D.
TO THE FBI?
- NO.
- RIGHT.
BECAUSE IT'S BULLSHIT.
YOU HAVE YOUR SUSPICIONS,
YOU COME TO ME.
- I TRIED.
- AND WHEN I SAY NO, QUINN,
IT'S OVER!
YOU'RE ON UNPAID SUSPENSION
UNTIL FURTHER NOTICE.
- SUSPENSION?
- JUST TELL EVERYONE YOU'RE
TAKING A FEW VACATION DAYS.
- YOU KIDDING?
- AM I FUCKING KIDDING?
YOU'RE LUCKY I DON'T
TERMINATE YOUR ASS.
AND YOU KNOW THE ONE REASON
I DON'T?
BECAUSE THERE'D BE
A MANDATORY HEARING,
AND THIS WHOLE EMBARRASSMENT
WOULD BECOME
A MATTER OF RECORD.
NO ONE NEEDS TO HEAR
ABOUT YOUR STUPID THEORIES.
IT WOULD TEAR
THIS DEPARTMENT APART.
UNDERSTOOD?
- SURE.
- HE JUST LOST HIS WIFE,
FOR CHRISSAKES!
- HEY, SKEEZEY...
WHERE YOU BEEN ALL DAY?
- VERY, UH, LONG,
FUCKED UP STORY.
I HEARD ABOUT THE RAID.
- PERP GOT AWAY.
- WHAT I HEARD WAS
YOU SAVED SOMEONE'S LIFE.
I LET YOU DOWN.
I SHOULD'VE BEEN THERE
TO BACK YOU UP.
- YEAH, YOU SHOULD'VE.
- YEAH.
YOU OKAY?
- I GUESS NOT, 'CAUSE EVERYBODY
KEEPS ASKING ME THAT.
I DON'T WANT TO BE ALONE
TONIGHT.
- DEB, I'M, UH...
NO GOOD FOR YOU.
- I'M NOT LOOKING
FOR GOOD RIGHT NOW.
[crickets chirping]
- IS THAT TRUE...
WHAT YOU SAID
ABOUT YOUR WIFE?
- YES.
- HOW DID IT HAPPEN?
- KNIFE.
PAINFUL AND CRUEL.
- I'M SORRY...
THAT I CUT YOU.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
A MONSTER, LIKE BOYD.
GONNA KILL ME.
OR WORSE.
I WAS LOCKED UP.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE,
OR FOR HOW LONG.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT
IT WAS HORRIBLE.
AND I THOUGHT...
IT WOULD NEVER STOP.
- BUT IT HAS STOPPED.
HE'S DEAD. IT'S OVER.
YOU CAN GO HOME.
- I DON'T THINK SO.
- YOU CAN.
I READ YOUR LETTER. I KNOW
YOU HAVE A FAMILY WHO LOVES YOU.
YOU SHOULD GO HOME TO THEM.
- IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE.
- IT IS.
IT REALLY IS.
- BOYD WASN'T THE ONLY ONE
WHO DID THIS TO ME.
THERE WERE OTHERS.
IT'S NOT OVER.