- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Andy time for your first injection.
Motherfuckers, you put me out.
Andy you are given instructions
and they must be followed.
I want to see Vladimir
right now, right fucking now.
Of course, just relax.
We need to check your vitals
and take some more blood.
Then I'd be happy to call Vladimir.
Fine, but you won't put me out,
and you won't put me under again.
Do you understand me?
It is our house rules to do
what's best for the treatment.
So I can't promise you that.
Dr. Vladimir, we need
you in Andy's room now.
Andy what's going on?
Are you okay?
Andy, when my team gives
instruction and you do not comply,
that is a problem.
We do not want to see you get hurt.
I just, I guess control of my body.
Yes, I understand that.
It may seem their tactics are unorthodox
but I can promise you, your time is
of great importance and value.
Allow me them to share a story
of my son and the importance
of spending time with someone.
Just like in this lab...
you are a family here, Andy.
We value your time as we
sacrifice our own time to ensure
that you can lead a much better life.
Well, what'd you learn from the story?
Sometimes we forget family
is more important than work.
One evening; I was coming
home from work late tired...
I found my five-year-old son
waiting for me at the door.
My son said, "Daddy,
may I ask you a question?
I replied "Yes, son, what is it?"
My son said, how much do
I make an hour at work?
I replied, "None of your business, son."
He continued and continued and said,
"Daddy, please, tell me how
much do you make an hour?"
I replied, "If you really must know
I make 100 dollars an hour."
He then looked up at me
and asked to borrow $50.
I replied, if you want the
only reason you asked me
was to buy some silly little
toy then march yourself
to your room and go to bed right now."
My son rushed to his room.
I was confused at first
and started to think
maybe he needed to
buy something important
as he never asks for money.
So I had rushed upstairs
to his room, open the door.
And asked if he was still awake.
He replied, "Yes,
Daddy, I'm still awake."
I said, "I had a very long day at work
and I took my aggravation on you
here is the $50 you asked for."
My son was excited at first
and thanked me for the money.
It's what he said and
did next that reminded me
of that time and importance of family.
So what was it that
he said and did next?
Uhmm...
In that moment he
reached under his pillow
and started peeling apart
some crumbled up bills.
He had saved for quite some time.
He then started to
count the money he had.
I was confused at first
and asked him why he needed more money,
if he already had some.
He said, "I didn't have
enough, but I do now."
I replied, "Enough, enough for what?"
He said, "I have a 100 dollars.
Can I buy an hour of your time?"
So you see, Andy, just like this story,
we must learn to trust each other.
As we all have a common goal.
I see... I definitely
appreciate everyone here.
We're glad to help, come
back next week during the week
on Monday after 5:00 p.m.,
we will do another injection.
Okay.
Can I help you, missy?
Hey yeah, I can just get
a small cheese pizza to go.
- Small cheese pizza?
- Yeah.
Sure, do you wanna wait for
it? Or do you wanna come back?
- I'll wait.
- Okay. Have a seat.
- Okay great thank you.
- It's on its way.
Great, thanks.
- Yes.
- Mr. Gaines...
I have Veronica on line one for you...
Thank you.
Hunter Gaines Investigation,
how can I help you?
Hi my name is Veronica and I work with
Rebecca Haines at Channel Four News.
I need some help with some
surveillance, can you help?
Sure, let's meet and discuss further.
When it's good for you, Veronica?
How is so one o'clock tomorrow?
1:00 p.m. is good.
Let's meet at Baki's at
1250 North Main street
in West Hartford, Connecticut.
It's just down the road from my office.
I'll meet you inside.
Again you're late.
What's going on?
I gotta tell you guys something.
I've been keeping this
secret for a very long time.
I'm sorry you have to hear this but.
Whatever it is... it will be okay...
We're here for you.
Dad, are you okay?
You're crying.
I went to the doctor
and it didn't go so well.
The doctor said I have
stage four brain cancer.
- You'll be okay, come on guys.
- And I don't know
how much longer I'm gonna be here.
Oh babe, you'll be okay.
All right guys, don't
worry, your dad's strong.
He's a fighter...
You know what? The game is coming on...
why don't you invite
some friends from work,
you can invite the neighbors,
you can invite some friends.
Just to get your mind off this okay?
All right, can I talk to him?
Why don't you go to your room, okay?
Why don't you sit down?
I love you.
Sergeant, what's the news for today?
I've heard from Sergey...
our loyal mercenary.
He's the one who's been
keeping tabs on Andy.
And?
You see the man in these photos.
He's been following
Andy, just as we have.
Who is he?
He's a private investigator.
Do we know who hired him?
Yes.
Who?
A Rebecca Haines, a news reporter.
I see.
Call Sergey... eliminate both targets.
Call me when it's done.
And another thing notify
Vladimir of this situation.
Right away, understood.
Hey babe, are you okay?
Babe, are you okay?
What's going on?
What's going on, man?
No.
- Snap out of it.
- Yes.
- You're all right?
- What's going on?
- Jesus Christ, Andy.
- What happened?
I think it's just better
everybody leave, I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- Oh my God, I'm sorry.
- Everybody leave.
- You all right?
Get up.
What?
Kids you should go upstairs.
Guys, I'm really sorry,
you need to leave.
Jesus Christ, Andy, you've
realized what you just did?
No. What happened?
It's like you were out of it.
The national Anthem came on,
it's like you were in a different world.
You don't remember that.
I must have had an injection
from one of the doctors.
I... did I black out?
Andy my friend was sitting next to you,
you grabbed a knife and attacked him.
You don't remember that?
Oh my God.
I'll tell the doctors
about this tomorrow.
Okay, Andy, oh my God.
What is going on?
We'll get through this babe, I promise.
Hello.
- Andy.
- Yes, that's me.
My name is Veronica and I work
for Rebecca Haines, we're
with Channel Four News.
Red Star Telecommunications
is not what you think it is.
And what do you know?
You're in danger.
This phone is likely being
tapped and you're being watched.
So I've left a note in your mailbox
with instructions on where
to meet me, come alone
and leave now.
Okay, I'll see you soon...
Okay.
- Andy.
- Yes.
Hey, so I'm Veronica with
Channel Four News, we spoke.
Yup.
We're probably being watched right now
so I'm gonna make this very brief.
Everything you're being told is a lie.
How do you know you me?
It's not what's important, just
read what's in the envelope.
Do you think Andy was convinced?
Of course Andy believed the doctor
he was very convincing, delivering
the fake news of brain cancer.
Brain cancer...
Damn it. If I didn't have cancer,
what the fuck were
they injecting me with?
Any other pressing matters?
Yes, sir we have an issue, sir.
What now?
Somebody has been stealing money
from our international accounts.
- Stealing?
- Yes, sir.
In my house?
Who has got the fucking
balls to steal from me?
Somebody has been stealing
from the online portal.
How much?
2.5 million U.S. dollars.
Get Boris in here now.
Yes, sir.
2.5 million bucks. How do
you steal 2.5 million bucks?
- How's that... ?
- We're gonna find this guy.
And break his legs...
he will never walk again.
I hope so.
While we're waiting on Boris.
Are there any other
pressing matters today?
Yes... the news
reporter... Rebecca Haines.
She's digging into us, sir.
Who's in the picture?
This car appears to belong
to a private investigator.
Some type of contact we
think is working for the CIA.
Yeah I know, I've put
Sergey on this earlier today.
Excellent I will follow it up, sir.
Very good, Vladimir.
Keep me posted, all right?
Yes.
What account got hacked?
The Hygate fund, Hygate.
Okay, I'm gonna get a list of all
clients who've paid into Hygate fund.
And I'm also gonna need to know
how they paid into the account.
Okay, so we have some clients
that pay through the online platform.
Right. That you secured for us...
Is that the only source for you?
Do you remember?
I sure do yeah, I'm gonna need
a list of all dates and times
from the funds went missing.
I'll then cross reference the
list with IP hits on the website.
If he stole once it's
bound to happen again.
I'll also insert a Trojan
to trick the hackers.
The next time he tries to
steal, I'll know his location.
As a matter of fact, he's
trying to steal right now.
Okay, I'll have his location soon...
Okay, the IP is tracing back to 4598
South Crenshaw Circle Boston, MA.
Name on the apartment
lease is Roman Ponomarev.
Vladimir send Sergey with
his federal credentials
and bring this person to me ASAP.
Yes, sir, I will call Sergei now.
Sergei 4598 South Crenshaw Circle...
Boston, MA...
He's a hacker named Roman.
Use your federal
badge, bring him here...
Go now...
Understood.
Hello, you Roman?
Yes, can I help you?
I'm Jack Collins... I'm with the FBI
I'm here to escort you to our
field office for a few questions.
I'm not going anywhere...
You have warrant?
I know the law I need a lawyer.
You're coming with me.
I'm not going anywhere.
I thought you were a hacker...
No. I got out of that business.
You are coming with me.
I'm not going anywhere... Fuck you!
You, I said you're coming with me.
I told you, you're coming with me.
Fuck you.
- Let's fucking go.
- Motherfucker.
So you're the guy who thinks he can hack
into my systems and steal from my boss?
Wait, wait.
I thought this was government building.
Why does it say Red Star
Communications outside?
You know... I'm a lawyer, right?
Why?
Because I own this place
and I control the
Russian Federation army.
Mr. Jack Collins here,
he's obviously not with
the FBI, he's my mercenary.
I send him out to kill
people, but in your case,
I wanted to chat with the little piece
of shit that stole from me.
Guys, I do not want any trouble.
I will give back what I take.
Wrong, Roman Ponomarev...
Let's see, you were born in Moscow,
arrived in the United States.
What, nine years ago?
See, I take these crimes personally.
Do you know anything about the
Japanese history and culture Roman?
No, I do not know this history.
Well, I do. Vladimir would be so kind
to tell him the story of
Lord Nishiki from the 1800s?
Yes.
There is something in which each
and every young samurai
should pay attention...
During times of peace
while listening to stories
of battle ... one should never say
when facing such a situation.
What should the person do?
Just like our little situation today.
You see such words are out the question.
How does a man who has doubts be
in his own room ... achieve
anything on the battlefield?
There is a saying that goes no matter
what the circumstances might be
one should be of the mind to win.
One should be holding the
first spear to strike...
Even though you put your
own life on the line.
There is nothing to be done.
When the situation
doesn't go as planned.
Do you feel any different
from your injections?
Well, besides your eyes.
I feel like a mutant now.
I have a red eye.
Let's get something to eat.
What is it, Andy?
Nothing I had thought I saw something...
It's nothing, I'm just hungry.
Let's get something to eat.
Welcome to Whitney Donut,
we'll be right with you.
Yes. We are ready... I'd like
to have a blueberry muffin
chicken sandwich,
chicken cutlet sandwich,
apple fritter, Roast Beef
sandwich and a root beer...
That's 17.42, please pull up...
Okay, thank you.
That'll be 17.42.
Die Andy die.
Don't worry Dawn, I'll
get us out of this mess.
Andy what is going on?
I can't tell you.
None is supposed to know0
I don't know how they, no
God damn Russians know...
They know my secret.
What's your secret?
I can't tell you, I can't tell anybody.
It's okay whatever this
is, I'm here for you.
You're gonna be okay.
Fucking Russians.
What's happening?
Dawn!! Dawn... Dawn where are you?
Answer me.
Dawn!!
Time to die for mother Russia.
No, no, no, Nora no.
No baby, I wouldn't hurt you.
I love you, no.
Hello, hello?
It is 17.42.
Snap out of it.
- You're all right?
- Yes, I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
There you go.
Thank you.
So you got the spear, are you gonna
draw first blood, and strike me?
No, I will not.
I'll give you your money back.
This is where you lose.
Looks like I've got the
first spear to strike.
You motherfucker, I will destroy you.
Don't make threats you cannot keep
say another word and
I'll cut out your tongue.
You were given a chance you've failed.
Look at his face.
Roman, seeing I am a
businessman and not a killer,
I'm gonna forget your failures
and I'm gonna give you two other
chances to walk out of here.
But this time when I tell
you something, you do it.
Dimitri would you be so kind
as to tell Roman the story
of the 10 blind masseuse?
My pleasure.
Once in the 1800s there was a group
of 10 blind masseuses
traveling along the mountains
and they began to pass
by the top of a precipice.
They became very cautious.
Their legs shook and in general
they were struck with terror.
But then the leading man stumbled
he fall off the top of the cliff.
Those that remain wailed...
Ahhh...
How piteous?
Don't be afraid...
Although I fall, it was for nothing.
I am now much rather
at ease before I fall
I think to myself, what
will I do if I fall?
And there was no end to my anxiety
but now I am much more settled.
What the fuck? Why are these lights off?
Vladimir, grab Roman
before he runs for it.
Is this the work of
the federal government?
Are they fucking with me?
Or did I forget to
pay the electric bill?
Duncan shall we use the room
upstairs off the power grid?
Dimitri, stay here with
the Sergeant and Sergey
and find out why these lights are off
call or text me when it's fixed.
Everyone else Let's bring
this piece of shit upstairs.
Vladmir take him
upstairs will follow you.
Let's go, Roman, try anything funny,
and I'll carve you like an
American Thanksgiving turkey.
Don't test me, move.
Ladies follow us up the stairs...
Do you mind?
Okay, Boris, Roman,
here's the challenge.
The closed circuit TV is
fixed on Leonard and Walker.
We're gonna fix on
yesterday at 4:03 p.m.
The first one that can show
me that footage at 4:03 p.m.
within 10 minutes wins.
Fair enough?
A piece of cake.
No problem.
But it's not gonna be that easy
while this is going my two
beautiful Russian ladies
Ivankov and Valeryie...
will be throwing Ninja
stars across your line
of vision at the pieces of wood
where they're being held by
Vladimir and Claude there.
And five, four, three, ...
two, one go.
It's done.
Let me see, he's right.
Boris has accomplished the task.
Well done, Boris.
Looser.
All right let's see these boards...
- Yes, sir.
- Claude, bring it over here.
Wow I can't tell the difference.
They're both excellent.
Bunch of center shots, I guess
it's gonna pay both 10 grand.
- Valeryie, great job.
- Thank you.
Ivankov... for you.
Well, the power should be back up again.
Let's move back downstairs.
Vladimir, grab this piece of
shit and bring him downstairs.
Yes, sir.
Don't mess with Dimitri.
Damn the game really is over
now for you, right, Roman?
Boris can you get this
piece of shit accounts,
and get my money now?
Sure, consider it done.
Dmitri, you and Vladimir get the bats
and break this fucking guy's legs
and then throw him
in a taxi and send him
to the nearest hospital.
No please, please...
I get you your money.
Orders are orders.
No, stop that, please stop, I beg.
No.
Welcome, Andy.
I think you're kind of early.
- Why don't you have a... ?
- Fuck off.
Andy, Andy, what's the matter?
Andy what are you doing here?
- Where's Vladmir?
- Help us get outta here.
Natayli, Natayli, get him out now...
What are you doing to these people?
Hey, hey.
Stop resisting us, you're ours.
Andy I told you not to come down here.
Now you'll have to deal with Valkov.
She's gonna kick your ass.
Andy put your hands in the air.
Fuck off. I am going to the press
and blowing this whole thing open...
Security, can I get
some security down here?
So, one of these kids said
she can kill with a spoon...
Yeah, I've heard that.
They're all watching us now,
we must be ready and
prepared for any raid...
I need a volunteer.
- No fucking way.
- I'm up.
- Anybody else?
- No fucking way.
Duncan why are you shaking your head?
I know you can kick my ass
- but I've got a challenge for you.
- I'm listening.
I'll bet you that I can
knock down your Ninja star
before it hits it's target.
Okay, on a count of three we go.
Okay.
Three, two.
There's a lesson to be learned here.
Huh?
The element of a surprise is a must.
Real classy, Duncan...
Always one step ahead...
- Hey, enjoy your training.
- Mm-hmm.
Here's the increased dosage.
Andy will soon become disoriented
and think today was all in
his head an hallucination.
Good, good.
Andy, Andy, Andy, Andy.
Andy, Andy...
... Andy?
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -