just like that everything changed
at that terrible moment in our hearts we
knew
home was a pen
humanity cattle
my brothers, for humanity
we should get back
I'm not but I just it's like the dream I
was having one on forever it's gone now
what was it about
Eren have you been crying
ribbon rock, stone, no my brethren they're
bastions of faith
might wanna have your dad
look into that
right just tearing up is usually a mental thing
hey Mr. Hannes
oh you just get on Mikasa's bad side
No, what're you even talking about
huh you smell like a tavern
the fully tears recovers an ale
of course
you kids care for a swig
aren't sure on watch?
Yep watch in the okay
We are thirsty work playing sentry
Pinochle only goes so far to chase off the boredom
Little nip now and then
keeps us all on our courage for a spell
Perks of being a guard
How do you expect to fight
if you're so loose on your feet
Huh
Now why on earth would I have to fight
what do you think what if they break
through the walls
we'd be sitting ducks on your watch
Eren,  kid please use your inside voice
Your doc's kid has some fire in him
Listen the only thing they've done to the wall
In the past hundred years is scratch at it
I have the feeling if they get
in their big heads to do something else
We'll be more than ready for him
A feeling? what if any of you actually done
To be ready for him
Dad says you've got a face sharp
Ah good dr. Yeager...yeah well
Can't argue with a man who's single-handedly
spared us from the plague
Thing is he's talking about his scalpel
What we do is in half as important
Hey no disrespect to your father
But a soldier's time beyond the wall
Kind of tends to put the whole issue
into a different perspective
You see him grooving around out there,
mindless dead-eyed
Wait a minute,
Sounds to me like you don't even think
that they're all that dangerous
Oh great, then at least have
the decency to stop calling yourself a garrison
People might get the wrong idea
Good point
Look at it this way huh
If a garrison is actually doing
what people think it oughta we're up a creek
Personally I take a lot of stock
In being called a freeloader means things are good
It's how I can measure peace of mind
Good we live in a cage
All we do is eat and sleep
That's it end of story
We have the peace of mind of livestock
Man you were right about the kid having fire
Careful not to cry it out
You coming back to the game or what ?
Yeah, hey where are you going?
The mouth on that kid
He's just a kid
Tends to dream bigger
than life really wants him to
Eren you should let
the Scout regiment thing go
Seriously? why does everybody think they're a joke
What people think about them isn't really the issue
Perfect timing
They're back we can make it if we hurry
get a move on I want a good view
I can't see spot
Sure taking a hit haven't  they?
yeah rest of them got eaten
That's what happens when pride takes you
outside the walls
Moses peg your pardon, where's my son
He should be with you all oh please tell me he made it
I wish I had better news
give it to her
I'm sorry it's all that was left of him
He did good yes, he was brave
Tell me my son stood his ground to the better end
that his death meant something
Tell me his sacrifice gave us a better chance
He was brave
But, his sacrifice did nothing
so with all our losses it's ever the same
Today with lost we have nothing
Your son died because of me
I sent him to his death
I sent all of them to their death
and there is nothing to show for it
All of them have mounts to nothing
Uplifting huh
Oh sure
Nothing like seeing our hard-earned taxes
Go toward keeping those bastards
fat and happy on human gris-
You little punk
What are you doing? let me go
yeah that's right you better run
Alright I get it stop already
Great firewood everywhere perfect
So are you still bound and determined
to become one of them the scouts?
Just help me pick thesis up
Like there is much to begin with
hey we're home
welcome back kids
Wow somebody worked hard to keep us in fuel for the next several days
whatever
what was that for your
Your earlobe's red which means you've got something to hide
Mikasa I helped you again now didn't she
hey where you off to dad?
a patient?
yes, some folks in the interior
should be back in about a week or so
so um Eren thinking about joining the Scouts
where do you keep secret, mouth?
get that ridiculous thought out of your head this instant young man
no son of mine is going to be fodder
do I make myself absolutely clear
stop yelling at me
-don't you dare
-it's a nightmare Eren the outside you really have no idea
yeah i get it okay but
but it's gotta be better than this life I'm not stupid
I know it's ugly out there I know
there's death around every corner but
We can't just give up on it
'cuz otherwise
this nightmare never gonna end
I see
Excuse me I'll do late for the fair
darling wait scold the boy for heaven's sake
Scold him? dear please
think this through
Mere words won't hold back the boy's curiosity
Eren, behave while I'm gone
And I'll let you in on what
I've been doing in the cellar
Agreed?
Yes sir you got it
Have a good trip
-I meant what I said
-What?
The whole idea is just irresponsible
Huh irresponsible?
so what it's more grown-up to settle for a living
In fear behind some stupid wall your whole pointless life
Eren
Mikasa the boy needs to be protected
from himself
Promise me whatever happens
I can count on you to have his back
Huh
Where's the sacrilege now huh
Or does your philosophy say it's wrong to fight back too
as a matter of fact it does
I'd rather take a few lumps and brawl like a beast
oh so now I'm a beast
Take a good hard look at yourself and tell me you're not acting like one
You resort to violence because your brains the size of a walnut
So pummel me all you want
I've already won yeah well you know what I'm a sore loser
Back off
It's Eren, okay look he's here back for more?
You think he would've learned his lesson?
Give this one to me oh crap she is with him
Just run
That's all it takes one look I'm just that scary
Well one of you is
Where'd they get you Armin ?
it's alright thank you
Okay
Oh they just heard me rattling
on about how man kind's future
Laid beyond the walls
Doubted they understood half of it
but still
idiots
Why is it gotta be this way
Why can't people just let us dream
The walls are a powerful idea
We've survived for a hundred years because of them
No one's keen on tempting fate
I may not agree with that sentiment
But I can see
where they're coming from
It's human nature Eren
When all said and done the government's policies
Are a reflection of our fear
Yeah the rest of the hurts
maybe I say to hell with them
Someone's gonna hear you
Keep it down
-Why would i care you rat me out either way
-What?
I never promised you anything
Your folks know about the scouts
Basically and they're not too pleased
Yeah big shock
It's sad but most people here are
willing to settle for
In exchange for some fleeting sense of security,
you know?
And make no mistake it absolutely is fleeting
The walls can't hold forever
Only a matter of time
Armin what are you doing
Talk to me what's going on is it kind of explosion or wha-
that's impossible
That wall's 50 meters high
Oh, God
It's a titan
It blasted a hole
Like it was kicking a rock
[people]: Run for your lives
It breaks through the wall
We have to go
Eren, no!
Our house is in that direction
Mom so is by herself
Mikasa!
This...this is the end
They're inside
We....every last one of us is going to be devoured
Our house is fine...our house is fine
You'll turn the corner and it's gonna be standing there in one piece...just like always
Mom!
Eren wait
Eren: Mikasa...grab that and then hoist with everything you got
Oh no!
Eren: Hurry up! damn it
Mikasa: I'm trying
It's them....you've got to get out of here
Eren just take Mikasa and run..Now!
Eren: I want to more than anything but first i need you on your feet
Sweetie listen to me my legs have been crushed
Even if you could get me out of here I can't run
There's no time
Eren: whatever i can carry you
Well you can just shut up and listen to me
For once in your life
One thing I'm asking you one thing make
Mikasa make him
Mikasa: i can't
You want all three of us to die
Hannes !
take the children and get them out of here
come on Karla that's not our only option
Hannes: Hey I'm a trained soldier my skill set
is killing Titans and saving lives
Karla: No wait don't do this please
nothing fits you just take it down get
all three of them out of harm's way
Pay good on the debt you owe
Eren: No ..what are you doing?
Put me down you bastard
Karla: Thank you Hannes
Eren: wait...No!
We cant just leave her
Karla: I love you
You hear me? stay alive
Karla: Don't leave me
Eren: Stop it! No!
It just like that everything changed
At that terrible moment in our hearts we
knew home was a pen....humanity cattle
Shiganshina  crumbles prayers are
useless tears are absurd
Death achenes are nothing
When total ruin is your reality
All that's left of any value is revenge