Wake up, Armin hey can you hear me
come on snap out of it
I need you to talk to me say something
There you are you with me now ? what's going on?
-Where's your squad ?
-Squad!
All right let's get you on your feet
You shouldn't be out here alone
What the hell you got all over you, that's so damn slimy
What happened?
[Armin]: You're worthless why can't you just die
[Connie]: Hey you need to pull yourself together
[Armin]: Damn you
[Connie]: Where is everyone?
Let it go Connie
-He's it the rest of them are dead
-Damn it don't talk like that we can't assume
he's the only one
Take a look around you isn't it obvious
We can't waste any more time here with
him we've got to move on
You're not making any sense
why would the Titans ignore him
I don't know maybe they thought
he was already dead or something
When you get right down to it that's the real tragedy here
Eren and the others bust their asses
and the one left standing is him
Alright that does it bitch
I'm gonna shut your mouth up permanently
Both of you stop it right now
We all at the end of our tether okay
We're seeing our friends being killed like animals
it's normal to be upset
Look at my Christa keeping the peace
You are so gonna have to marry me
when all this crap is over
Yeah well should best get a hold of that mouth
All right come on we got to get out of here
You able to stand?
Sorry for being non sense
Don't worry about me
I was wrong this world hasn't become hell
It's been hell i just couldn't see it before now
We're condemned all of us have been
from the beginning
Strength preys on weakness
It's a very straightforward arrangement actually
But...My friends they...
They tried
They knew how the world worked
They wanted to be strong for me
someone who only brought them down
In their eyes i was the  victim I needed protection
But all i wanted was to stand shoulder to shoulder
with them, to be strong like they were
To be worth something
Hell this is how it all ends up
Eren dragged to protect meand-
Hanna, what're you trying to do?
Oh God Armin Help me please
Franz couldn't breath in and i can't wake him up
He won't response to CPR
C'mon baby you got this stay with me
Somebody help us
Hanna please, it's not safe on the ground
We need to get you to the rooftop-
No I'm not leaving him like this
You really don't understand, do you?
Hanna I'm sorry Franz is-
Please stop
Please stop doing that
I can't
I can't take it
This is Hell
What the hell is wrong with you people I don't think
you fully appreciate how bad the situation is
Oh I appreciate it just fine believe me
You wanna make it out of here alive
stop whining and help
You're a soldier do something
Make him move that damn wagon
-I'm not exactly sure I...
-Take your best shot little man
I'm the president of this town's merchant guild
Uh well I...
Who do you think pays all the bills for
the food you and your buddies crap out
Or maybe you got some finances clubs
a way to fund the racket you call a job
Now shut up and push this cargo's worth
more than you people make in your whole lives
Nobody's getting out of here unless the
wagons in front of them
There's a reward in it if you help
don't worry sweetheart
Daddy's gonna use those Big Loud cannons
he showed us to scare the Titans off
Mommy look
There
Push it through dam it
If you don't that thing is gonna kill us all
Someone wanna tell me
why this son of a bitch is ignoring us
It's an abnormal stop trying to figure him out
He is too fast there is no way we will ever take him before he reaches the gate
Just stay on him
Excuse me, what is all this?
Couldn't have asked for better timing
Force these useless morons to push my wagon
I'll pay you handsomely
Seriously soldiers are dying back there
Laid out their lives for you
All because this is taking too long
Yeah that's their job you expect me
to shed it to you because they gotta
Fulfill the duties they signed on for
they're supposed to be willing to lay
Down their lives
don't get all high-handed on me just cuz
You finally got to earn your damn keep
after all these years
Yeah no arguing with that you're
absolutely right sir
Guess it's what you call the greater good
Still sometimes it's not the life or the death of
a soldier that makes the biggest difference
Don't you even dare your commander
and I are old friends
One word from me and you'll be court-martialed
believe me
That word gonna come from beyond the grave?
No wait
Sir, maybe we should...
pull the damn wagon out
You're Amazing
You've saved our lives miss
all of us are in your debt
Good work Ackerman I'm impressed
I did what I could here sir
But thank you I need to be a bit more
careful in the future
I inadvertently dulled both of the blades
I'll do better next time
what on earth have you had to live to be so nonchalant
I'm sorry that was uncalled for
Why do I have to suddenly think of you now?
I'm finish mama
What do you think did I do good
Oh darling it's absolutely fantastic
Excellent work
Oh thank you
We've kept this style of embroidery a special
family secret for heaven knows how many generations
One day when you have children of your own
you'll be able to pass the secret on to them
Huh...I don't understand how can I have children
Uh honey why don't you explain?
Yeah please daddy
well I'm not sure I'm really an expert on this subject
but you know what that nice doctor Yeager scheduled
to pay us a visit today maybe you could talk to him
Haha speak of the devil
Just a moment
Her name is Mikasa?
Yes and she's just about your age
try to get along okay
There aren't that many children around here
and I'd rather you not grow up to be an outcast
If she's nice to me then we wont have aproblem
Eren look for the bad in people
expecting to find it and you will
Hmm...That's odd of them
Are they home?
Mr.Ackerman
It's doctor Yeager is anyone there?
Well are they aren't there?
Dad, what's wrong?
Dam it!
Look around can you see the daughter anywhere?
Perhaps she's outside
I don't think so
This is bad
I need to alert the military police
of this while the trails warm
wait for me at the foot of the mountain understood
Say that back to me word for word
Eren!
Uh-huh all I'm saying is she better go for a decent price
I didn't get blood on my hands for nothing
Look at her face and tell me what she's worth
Sure she's cute and all just young
wouldn't go for her myself
Then I guess we're lucky
you're not the one we're selling to
Plenty of folks who'd pay a premium
She's exotic what they used to call an oriental
You know about all that right
Back when there used to be different breeds of people
The bunch of him from the Far East
came scrambling here for safety
The old perverts in the capital
really go for that sort of thing
This little beauties gonna fetch a mint at auction
It's great business she's the last of her kind
all the rest of her people died out
Tell me another one it's not like she's
a pureblood or anything, her old man wasn't oriental
Good point there the mother
would have been a nice addition, right?
Too bad she's in pieces
Give me a break what was I supposed to do?
she was putting up a fight
So you couldn't have just knocked her unconscious?
We were just talking about you Doctor
Sorry hope we're not interrupting
let's take this nice and easy
I don't imagine anybody wants their skull open by this little guy
(The bitch is out of her mind)
Run Mikasa run as fast as you can
Stop it you're scaring me
I want you to be scared
Move it get away from here
Dad!?
Screw it
You ain't want this crap
You stupid bastard the plan must only kill the father
She was nuts I'm supposed to let her go caus-
-I don't give a shit just bag the kid
-Fine
Hey let's not give me any attitude all right
If you're feeling feisty this is what you get
So cold
I'm sorry
Don't move from that spot you little farming
How did you even find this place?
Uh..well I was..in the woods...got...lost
I saw your cabinet
Lost in the woods huh? Kid your age
shouldn't be out there on his own to begin with
Big bad wolves are liable
to pounce on you from out of nowhere
It's alright now you'll be safe here
my buddy and I'll be happy to take you-
I appreciate that sir, but I'm not stupid
And I'm the last thing you will ever see
What the hell do you think you doing?
Hey little bastard get back here
You're an animal, you hear me?
No, you're a disease
This is what you get you son of a bitch
This is what you get for being what you are
Die....Die
The hard part is over
You're safe now
Anyway Mikasa alright? my name is Eren
I'm dr. Yaegar's son
I met your folks once or twice while I was with him
We were stopping by your house today for a checkup
We saw
What happened to the third one
This is all your doing, isn't it
Answer me you little bastard
You did this
I'm gonna kill you
You gonna die
Tak-
Take him out
Fight
Kill or be killed
Fight for your life
It's..it's the only way
Who the hell do you think you are you little brat
The only way to live
Is to fight
I can't
I don't think I can do this
And all of a sudden...I remembered
I'd seen it all before
Many...many times
Since the day I was born
It'd been all around me, forever
But
I always look the other way
Yeah
The world is a cruel place
And it's home
All of a sudden my body wasn't shaking
I was in total control, focused, ready
All of a sudden I could do anything
Fight
Stabbed through the heart from behind
surely a couple of kids couldn't have done this
Damn it son, I made it clear
I wanted you to wait at the foot of the mountain
Do you even understand the magnitude
of what you've done here today
Sorry dad I'm not gonna feel bad for what happened
They were animals disguised as humans
who needed to be put down
-Listen to yourself
-By the time the military police got here
They'd have been long gone and you know it
We couldn't afford to wait
That's not what I'm arguing about
you threw caution to the wind and survived by pure luck
You're strong, yes. but you're too damn young
to be so casual about gambling with your life
I..I didn't know how I was supposed to save her
Mikasa, remember me?
We met a few times
before when you were just a tiny little thing
Yes dr. Yaegar
So umm.... sorry can you just tell me how to get home?
It's cold...I'm tired
There is really nowhere else for me to go
Don't worry you can keep it
That ought to keep you warm right?
I think so
Mikasa, how would you feel
about coming to live with us?
What?
I can't even imagine what you've been through
But I do know you need your share of rest
What's the problem?
Don't think about it just come on
We gotta get home
Yeah Okay
The world's a cruel place
if you want to live you have to fight
That's it we're done
Now scale the wall
I should help the Vanguard withdraw, sir
Ackerman wait
It's a cruel world but by have a place in it
Eren as long as you're part of my life
I can fight to the bitter end
It's a cruel world but by have a place in it
Mikasa races through hell to be besides
the one person who make the struggle worth while
Only to learn just how deep hell goes