They first appeared over a hundred years ago
Giant humanoid creatures with a tease for our blood
The brute strength of these separations
trumped an average person's many times over
We were shoved to the brink of extinction
Almost overnight
The survivors erected walls
Maria, Rose and Sina
Withdrawing behind them and frightened Huddle's
For what was to be a century of uneasy peace
And then
The Titan assault on Trost left us reeling owing at least
in part to the Scout regiments absence at the time
Military casualties were...profound
Ironically they'd embarked on a
reconnaissance mission beyond the wall
that very morning
Heads up the main unit of the Scout
regiment is back
That's right commander Erwin
did you give those ugly bastards a thrashing?
Look it's captain Levi
They say he's like an entire brigade to himself
spare me please
That scowl will crush your fans not any of my business
But from a public relations standpoint you might like not
Wow the threshold of Titania
Can't you just envision the horrors
that stow for us comrades ?
I'm on pins and needles
we bagged an abnormal embarrassed with tears
I think we've bagged the craziest abnormal already
What's seriously? where ?
I mean you
Move out
The Scout regiments primary function is
to establish bases of expansion
Acting as a spearhead for human knowledge
theirs is a solemn and dangerous honor
Thanks to the ingenuity of its exemplary members
the regiment's survival rates have improved
That said, excursions into long relinquished territory
still  commonly result in a death toll exceeding 30%
A stark illustration of the disparity
between our own strength
And that of the Titans
One day...one day you will all just be a bad memory
Mankind will destroy all of you
Mark my words the last one standing
Will be us
Of course why you'd care, you bastard
Just wait till captain Levi
One on the right, two on the left
[Petra]: Captain the reinforcement are here sir
Good tent to our comrade below Petra
You two, take out the Titan to your right
The pair on the left belongs to me
Captain wait
Don't be scared big guy I wont hurt you
cross my heart and hope to die
See? bet you barely felt a thing
I mere you can't help being headless
But I can't help being tired of looking at you
Uh oh, easy big stuff
nobody's got time for crybaby
Let's take it like a man shall we?
Disgusting
[Petra]: Captain I...I can't stop the bleeding
Captain...Levi
I'm here
Did...
Did this...make a difference?
Was that...
Was that helpful?
Please, sir...
Don't tell me this was for nothing
Tell me this life is the cost
We've made great strides today soldier
and tomorrow, because of you
Your strength won't die with you
the torch will be carried on by me
This I swear on my very life
the Titans will be eradicated
Sir
I'm sorry, he's...
Did the man hear what I had to say? any of it?
Yes sir, matter of fact I think he heard all of it
Look at him that's a face at peace
We can help
[Erwin]: Levi
We're pulling out
Sir ?
What do you mean? you damn well know
that we can push further
My men didn't die to pave our retreat
[Erwin]: There's a swarm of Titans moving north
they're bearing down on the city
It's just like five years ago
Something tells me this is going to be bad
For all we know the walls
already been reduced to rubble
Damn you
This...this isn't real
We were ready...we were ready
We had the books we trained
This isn't a mystery to us anymore
We knew how to beat them
How to survive
Help me...it's soo hot
I need to go home
Mom would be worried
I hope she went home
Oh...mom
Help me...please
How has it come to this?
why has everything been taken from us
Our lives
Our dreams
Everything
Damn you...damn you all to hell
I refuse to die like this
I'll drag them all out, kill them with my bare hands
Do you hear me?
With my bare hands
This isn't your world...not anymore
I'll kill every last one of you
Get up
Let me kill you again, and again, and again
You're mine all of you
You're all gonna die
Eren?
You're right ?
Look at me Eren hey can you move ?
Can you hear me ? say something listen
you've got to tell them everything
They're terrified but they'll understand
Armin why...
You catch that he said we're all gonna die
There's not much else you can make of that
Son of a bitch wants to eat us you watch
What the hell are they talking about
What is this
Why are all their blades pointed at us
Those are meant for taking down Titans
What's going on ?
And what's with that look
Are they terrified of me?
I want all you cadets on standby look sharp
If we hadn't found the gas
we'd have never gotten out of a Trost
Basically we got lucky that's it
That sounds terrible I'm so sorry
We volunteered to run supplies out to everyone
but the situation was so bad
We did even found some gas we were gonna
dole out to you guys but then everything went to hell
So you're saying everyone who isn't here now
didn't...uh you know
Yeah
Wait what about Mikasa ?
Huh yeah no no she's good she made
it in after us with the group Jean led
Hey Jean where in the world's Mikasa
she got hurt or what ?
hey talk to us
I would tell you if I could
they slapped us with a gag order
Whoa you're joking right ?
That's nuts
They're nuts if they think people aren't gonna talk
or it'll get out, and when it does
Well that is if we survive
You gotta hand it to the engineering corps for putting
the heap of rents at Titan corpses to good use I suppose
Still just a barricade though
we can't get too comfortable
Stay on your toes whatever happens next
it's bound to happen here
This is the proverbial line in the sand
Hey something wrong ?
Sir, my apologies I completely agree
I'm just a little preoccupied about my friends in the vanguard
There was a messenger on the way to HQ
with this look on his face
Kid, difficult as it may be you've got to wrangle
your mind to stay focused on what's here in front of us
Is it true what they say about you
saving those kids five years ago, sir ?
They're cadets now right ?
won't they be at the vanguard too ?
That's right ?
I'm really sorry, sir
Don't know why I felt the need to bring it up
[Hannes]: They are good
Some tough little bastards believe me
they know what it takes to stay alive
One of them's just about the best fighter I've ever seen
The other so stubborn
it can drive you crazy Loads of inner strength
And their friends a certifiable genius
They will be fine, not a doubt in my mind
Cadets Eren jaeger, Mikasa Ackerman and Armin Alert
The three of you have jointly committed an act of high treason
Whether or not the swift execution
as a result depends on you
What?
Any attempt to move from where you stand now
Anything I deem at least bit suspicious
will be met with cannon fire, do not test me
Answer carefully Eren Jaeger
what exactly are you ?, human or Titan ?
What is that supposed to mean ?
why they all glaring at me like that ?
It's like...like they're looking at a monster
Oh God, is that what they think?
I'm sorry, sir I don't understand
Son of a bitch is playing innocent
Answer me damn you evasion
will get you nowhere
Don't try to stall it pretend ignorance
Won't stand a chance you'll be blown to hell
before you can assume your true form
What true form ?
Please the all of us saw it happen
You emerge from the carcass of a fallen Titan
in full view of your comrades
A creature of unknown origin ability or a legion
to slip through and infiltrated wall Rose
And that creature is you
Under the circumstances you're being
sanctioned by His Majesty is neither here nor there
You are risk and I willing with my rights to eliminate
I will not let the situation stand
Every moment I squander mulling
over your supposed innocence
Puts us all in further jeopardy
from attack by the Armored Titan
Hell we're all I'm aware you're attached
to diversion precisely for that purpose
I'm sorry humanity's fate hangs in the balance
I cannot waste any more time or manpower on you
Do you understand ?
my conscious will not falter to watch you die
[Rico]: Nor should it, as soldiers
they all know the price of their position
If they're this committed to defiance
under threat of death so be it
They won't be persuaded,
and as you say it's just a waste of time
Sir, please this may be our best chance
Will expend far less artillery if he's in human form
Excuse me I wouldn't not while I'm standing here
Unless anyone's feeling up to the task in which case
well, I'm happy to demonstrate my own technique
On you and every last inch of your traitorous flesh
Sir, there's something you should know
She was assigned to the elites fresh out of training
Equal to a hundred soldiers easily
if we lost her it'd be quite the tragedy
Okay somebody talk to me now the
The hell is all this
Mikasa you can't take them all on
Even if you took down a few
there's nowhere left for you to run
Whoever comes at Eren deals with me
I'll take on the entire regiment if I have to
I don't give a damn what they tried it through with us
This isn't the only way they're just scared
they don't understand what's happening
we need to calm down and just talk it out
Am I the only one here
who doesn't think I'm a Titan ?...damn it
Why can't I remember how I got here
Too weak to stand up and if I say the wrong thing ...
Is this it for me ?, killed by people ?
What was that he said about me
coming out of the Titan carcass in front of everyone
Is he insane ?, why is no one making any sense ?
That was all just a dream...
Or
No
My sleeve...my arm
Am I really one of them?
It's not possible it's just now...
One more time...are you a human being or Titan?
I...I don't know what to say
my life is not the only one at stake
But I mean...I've always been...one of you
I'm Human
So you say, I'm left with no choice
Forgive me
If push comes to shove
All of us are monsters
Armin head for the wall
I've got Eren
Wait, no...ah
[Grisha]: Eren
Behave while I'm gone and
I'll let you in on what I've been doing in the cellar
Listen to me it's vital
that you keep this key on you at all times
Whenever you look at it let this thought
flood over you...I must return to that cellar
I'm going to give you a little something
to make you forget for the time being
I'm sorry I wish there was more time to
explain all this when the time comes though
Know that you must reclaim wall Maria
and head for the cellar
Won't both be pleasant but in my heart
I know what I'm doing is for the best
When the ability confuses you let
their memories act as your guide
Eren!
One day the truth will come out I swear to you
The journey will be a painful one but it is yours to make
Mikasa's life, Armin's life everyone's life
It is on your being able to control this power
Did we get him?
Dear God
Armin pleads for the life of his friend
desperate to convince their comrades
Eren isn't the monster he seems
but however eloquent however passionate
Reason finds no hold and Minds wracked by fear