Edited at https://subtitletools.com
In the year 845,
Two terrifying new breeds of Titan appeared
The Colossal and the Armored
Barreling through the outer walls as if wholesale destruction was child's play
In blood and thunder our way of life ended
The Titans spent their hunger
for human flesh unchecked
The territory counted within the circle of wall Maria was abandoned
20% of the human race perished
As the Titan onslaught advanced our only choice
was to his draw behind Wall Rose
pick up the pace you led heeled laggards
Your boots waterlogged Arlert?
Let's see some hustle !
they're too heavy for you son?
Hell drop it leave it in them by
The Titans are easy if they were digesting you
without all the excess baggage
Seriously?..here focus on staying upright we are being graded on this you know
- Thank's but, won't they demerit you for helping me?
- Yeah if they find out
Just make the cut we're even alright?
Reiner Braun
The minded constitution of a grass-fed ox
Respected by his comrades
I'm no one's burden you hear me
Armin Arlert
Built like a daffodil but academically brilliant
Annie Leonhart
Gifted with a sword but does not exactly play well with others
Bertolt Hoover
Heaps of native talent but to mild-mannered
Jean Kirschtein
Head of the class on ODM also
An insufferable smart-ass with a hair-trigger temper
Think they'll show off some slice and dice
best hope you see a Titan before I do
Military Police, save a place for Jean
Why to leave the charge
You don't care if steal your thunder, right?
Sasha Blouse
Unusually find Instinct
Rarely shares them with her teammates
Connie Springer
Agile on the switchbacks
Few sandwiches shy of a picnic
Get ready
Damn it, still not  deep enough
Mikasa Ackerman
Model cadet, excels in everything
In fact it's no overstatement to call the girl a genius
Eren Yeager
Lackluster in the classroom marginally better in the field
But driven by a sense of purpose that's almost terrifying
Sorry man, I've really gotta learn to hold back
It's alright let's see how you do as a rogue
- What are you waiting on ?
- This training doesn't make sense
We're not exactly picking fights
with someone around our size
A guy have to be stupid to use this, I mean a knife
What if there's not an option
The fight doesn't give us a say
If it wants to get ugly it gets ugly
it's our job to be prepared
The enemy comes in many forms
artillery is not always gonna be the answer
Soldiers the ones worth their self anyway
Are ready for anything
Don't believe me? look
Yeah what about her
Only things she's ready for is any chance to slack off
You think so?
maybe somebody ought to give her a talking to-
-to give her a little hard knocks lesson
in preparedness
Common doubt not beating you down enough?
Keep it up you'll be as
flat as the dirt you're walking on
I suggest you think back to
why you enlisted in the first place
What are you doing?
Wow she's pissed
Wow I thought she looked scary before
He couldn't pay me enough to be on her bad side
-Okay, now go get her
-Huh, What the hell wait!
Right, I hope you don't expect me to hold back
Heads up!
AH! son of a-
That was a dirty move
Are we done here?
Not just yet, you know the drill
take up the dagger
No, wait!
This isn't help- oh CRAP
There
So you're ready to take me on yourself yet or what?
-Ah! Not exactly
-don't you dare
She's got a lesson coming right? you go get her
Yeah, a soldier can't really afford to back-down either
Get ready here I com-
That's some technique you've got
Who taught you to fight like that?
My father did
He like pioneer or -
Does it really matter
It's pointless just like all this
Wait you mean the training in general?
Hand-to-hand combat doesn't really count
against our final grade
The smart ones blow it off
It's a crapshoot anyway only the top ten cadets
get to serve in the interior the rest of us? forget it
Point is only the idiots like you take
this part of bootcamp seriously
Idiots, whatever they are
First rule of this life kid
The better you are at dropping the bad guys
The more distance the powers-that-be put
between you
That's what this whole stupid farce is about
sure whatever you say
Face it, you don't fight the nature of things and win
Look around you Eren, all the sons of bitches
really expect us to do is play the game
Don't be a pawn
Yeah well I still stand by what I said earlier
I've been so fixated on building myself up I couldn't see it
She's absolutely right
They're not honing their skills to fight,
They're honing their skill to run
I know okay and look I'm not saying it's right it's just the way things are
Before wall Maria was compromised
ODM experts were rare
only Scouts ever risk proximity to the Titans
(That's how you conserve fuel let your momentum do the work for you)
Still that's pretty advanced
duh it's called having a sixth sense
For the finer points of your gear
You gotta do the strut if you want to make the cut
The MP only recruit the best
man that'd be amazing
Working within a stone's throw the king
No greater honor than that
Shut up Marco
We're not children you can drop the misty-eyed BS!
Honor doesn't have any damn part of it
You just want a nice cushy job in the interior playing glorified century
-That's not true That's not me at all
Listen to you guys
Interior five years ago this was part of it
you're gotta point to make friend? I'm right here
Poor Jean so misguided and besides
I don't think your head will fit in the interior anyway
Very funny seems a little backwards to me
Fine tuning your Titan killing skills so they Brass station you somewhere you'll never see one
you'd rather I was good at getting
killed thank you but I'll pass
-better to play the system than getting nod off
-Oh you son of a bitch
bring it on you little bastard
Eren please stop it
Gentlemen, please
You think you can Judge me?
-You ripped my shirt you damn
-I don't give a damn about your shirt you pissed me off
What are you crazy
oh wait I get it
He has something to prove sounds familiar
Sorry to do this
It's only to end this before things get out the hand
Damn it
What the hell was that move ?
Little something I picked up this afternoon
while you were busy with your thumb up your ass
You honestly believe the military police
are your ticket to the good life
You're not a soldier you're a joke
Would someone care to explain
the little ruckus I'd heard just now
I do hope everything's all right
-Sasha passed some gas commandant
-Why am I not surprised
For the love God learn some self-control
Of the original recruits
218 cadets graduated some with honors
Do you have heart
Sir!
As of this moment you have three options open to you
Choose wisely
The garrison regiment
Whose job is to reinforce the walls
The Scout regiment
Who rides out in a Titan's country to take back
what was once ours
And the MP regiment
Maintaining law and order under orders
from His Royal Majesty
Those cadets eligible for the MP
have already been named
The rest of you take a look
these are the top of your class
This is it we've made it
Our time is now
Titans be reay
Alright MP here I come
three square meals a day for life
How in God's name did I get ranked under Eren
You're really gonna turn your back on the MP
for the scouts?
Why in the world would you do that
you're in the top ten
the scouts have always been my goal
I don't want the easy life
not with all the work I've put in
I trained to fight Titans
Are you insane
How many people have died
we're talking a fifth of the population
If that doesn't paint a picture for you
I don't know what will
This is our life now we, can't beat them
Yeah so what we buckle take it all line down
Things have changed
maybe not a hell of a lot but enough
They aren't the mystery they were five years ago
There's still a long way to go but we've made progress
Every battle we lost taught us a lesson
Gave us the tiniest in road towards something like hope
You telling me it's better to cut our losses let all the death and destruction be meaningless
Just to ball it up and accept it not on your life
humanity's future lies outside the walls
and I'm gonna clear the way
I'm gonna take back what was ours
I'll Drive them out
And as long as at least one of us can say that
we're not done
Eren wait
Yeah good luck out there hotshot
I'll root free from his Majesty's barracks
-That was quite a speech you gave us there
-Yeah most of it was yours well
All that stuff you used to say back in the day
Yeah well I'm joining the Scout regiment too
Now you're just being stupid
come on you're not a fighter
-Your life is with books
-I'm through with letting other people fight for me
Guess it's the scouts for me too then
Oh come on you're top of the class
you'll be wasting your shot
Understand this Eren where you go I go
I made a promise to your mom before she died
I'm not letting you die
I've got your back whether you like it or not
so just deal with it
Yeah well mom's not here
A lot of people I used to care about aren't here either
Heads up the main unit of the Scout regiment is back
That's right commander Erwin
did you get those ugly bastards a thrashing?
Look it's captain Levi
They say he's like an entire brigade himself
-Spare me please
-Feel how excited everybody is?
It's like the crowd just has a different energy now
Well we are going on five years without incident
seems like a good omen
And you should check out all the cannon upgrades
the sight alone ought to be enough to scare them off
That's the truth
human denial cuz' you're a couple what's that about
Whow whow, this isn't what it's looks like okay
Knock it off man it's embarrassing
[Hannes]: Hey hey lookie here
[Eren]: Mr.Hannes
Word on the streets they let you graduate yesterday
Either you've grown up for a standards of plummeted
Oh yeah like you're one to talk the Corps
of engineers keep their new chief in the drink
Watch it
I'm sorry if this is out of the blue
but I want you to know your mom's death still haunts me
Me too but it wasn't your fault
We were shooting in the dark then
but nothing like that's gonna happen again
We know what we're dealing with now
Fred up and capable make a good combination kid
Don't screw it up by dying
What the hell you mean you're joining the scouts
-What happened to the MP that was your whole thing
-Don't worry about it
-The guy is allowed to change his mind, okay
-I think your speech yesterday lit a fire under him
Ain't nobody talking to you
his temper tantrum had nothing to do with it
Take it easy it's not like you're the only one
Why are you serious
Can you guys keep a secret cuz' i totally
just helped myself to the officers pantry
Sasha they can throw your butt in the clink for that
-Seriously what is wrong with you
-What isn't wrong with her
it'll be fine I'm willing to share
oh can you imagine the sandwiches
Put it back
Do you have any idea how rare meats been
since the Titans took wall Maria
Um a little bit yeah
Just look at it this way pretty soon
we'll take back all the room we need for livestock
-I would really like a slice please
-Hey if he gets one so do I just so you know
-Me too
-I'm in on it too
-But?
-Come on don't just stand there
If they see us slacking off, we're in for it
See you guys at lunch time
Has it really been five years
look at us ready to stand tall again
We can do it
Mankind didn't start this fight
but we are gonna finish it
Ah, It's Hot
Samuel!
Sasha!
Try not to move, understand
That was too damn close
Oh God no not again
They are gonna get in!
No, this is over
I'm gonna put a stop to this
I will
This ends now
This is it people
Do or Die
Mount to cannons squad four
Take out the Colossal Titan
This is our chance
Don't let it slip away
You, it's been a while
The jaws of hell re-open
before you can even catch your breath
your between its teeth
sometimes saving the people dearest to you
means making the ultimate sacrifice