They first appeared over a hundred years
ago
Giant humanoid creatures with a tease for our blood
The brute strength of these separations
trumped an average person's many times over
We were shoved to the brink of extinction
Almost overnight
The survivors erected walls
Maria, Rose and Sina
Withdrawing behind them and frightened Huddle's
For what was to be a century of uneasy peace
In the year 845,
Two terrifying new breeds of Titan appeared
The Colossal and the Armored
Barreling through the outer walls as if wholesale destruction was child's play
The territory counted within the circle
of wall Maria was abandoned
20% of the human race perished
As the Titan onslaught advanced our only choice
was to his draw behind Wall Rose
In the year 850
The Colossal appeared once again
Breaching the wall bordering Trost
before disappearing
The Titans flooded in through the broken gate
[Armin]: Eren, No
No
Two hours later the evacuation
of the entire populace was completed
As a result no civilians were lost to the Titans
The same cannot be said for the countless
soldiers who perished buying the people time
[Mikasa]: Eren as long as you're part of my life
I can fight to the bitter end
Captain please wait, there's only a handful of us left sir
If the Titans were to attack her in force
we wouldn't have a chance in hell of holding them off
Please sir we need you here
Out of my way soldier we have to get going my expertise
is needed to help direct the reinforcements
Behind the safety of the inner gate, Am I right?
Just what the hell are you implying
they need my help reorganizing
Or would you rather us be overwhelmed
due to your logistical nightmare
But sir if we lost those supplies
That's enough
Question my orders again will delay me of my duties
and I warn you treasonous high straight through
Why isn't anyone going over the wall?
They must have heard the withdrawal signal?
It's over
All over
We're doomed
There
C'mon now
That musket is not enough to stop them
Hey Jean what are we gonna do?
We can't do anything
They finally gave us the order to withdraw
And we were all out of gas of course
I can't believe this is how it's gonna end
because of those damned cowards
You mean the supply depot? what is going on?
Where are they?
They all lost their will to fight and I can understand why
But they abandoned their duty to supply us
Barricading themselves inside HQ
And of course Titans have swarmed the place
which means we can't get the gas ourselves
Then why are we waiting? we gotta go,
start sending their numbers so we have a chance
Sitting here on this roof is totally pointless
Eventually the Titans are gonna come for us
We don't have much gas left
we'll just waste what little we've got if we try to run
And without our mobility we're completely screwed
You're using your head for once Connie nice going
But I'm just not sure if we've got
the numbers needed to pull this thing off
The veterans and the Vanguard force have all been killed
How exactly do a bunch of rookies
pull off a suicide mission like this
I mean let's assume half of our force
even survives the initial assault
Then what? the supply room was probably
crawling with Titans in the three or four meter range
I don't see us accomplishing much in there
It's hopeless
God what a dull life this turned out to be
I never even got to tell her just how I feel
Come on guys we can do it right, let's go
If we all work together
we can make this happen, I know we can
All right?
I'll take the lead
Armin it's time to go
[Annie]: Reiner, do we move out?
[Reiner]: Not yet we have to let them gather up first
[Marco]: It's no use, there's too many of them
I don't think any of us are going to survive this
I've come to accept my pending demise
I just wanted my death to mean something
Mikasa, weren't you were the rearguard ?
Annie, I know how bad things have gotten
it's selfish putting personal matters in the forefront
But have you seen Eren's squad?
Some squads made it back
but I don't know about Eren's
We found Armin he's over there
Armin
Mikasa
I can't
How would I tell her what happened to Eren?
I survived, it means nothing
So useless
I wish I had died with him instead
Armin, are you okay?
you're not hurt are you?
Where's Eren?
Armin?
They were ..
The cadets of the squad 34
Thomas Wagner
Nac Tias
Mylius Zeramuski
Mina Carolina
Eren Yeager
These brave five upheld their duties
They died furiously in the field of battle
Please no
His whole squad was wiped out?
The same will happen to us
if we try to take on those Titans
I'm so sorry, Mikasa
It should've been me that died not Eren
I...
I couldn't do a thing
I'm worthless
Armin
Calm yourself we haven't got time
for you to get emotional right now
On your feet
Marco if we eliminate or bypass the Titans of HQ
we can there refuel our gear
Allowing us to get back over the wall
is that assessment correct?
Well yeah I guess so sure
But there's just too many of them out there
Even with you on point
I can do it
What?
I'm strong, real strong
None of you come close you hear me?
I am a warrior
Know this, I have the power
to slay all of the Titans that block our path
Even if I have to do it alone
As far as I'm concerned
I am surrounded by a bunch of unskilled Cowardly worms
You disappoint me you can just sit here
And twiddle your thumbs and watch how it's done
Wait Mikasa are you out of your mind? that's crazy
You can't be serious trying to take them out by yourself?
There's no way you could hope to beat them
If I can't beat them then I die
But, if I win I'll live
And the only way to win is to fight
Hey!
You know I was expecting something more motivational
Your way with words was kind of a little
I blame everything about this on you Eren
Hey don't just stand there, we weren't taught
to let our comrades fight alone
Unless you are a coward
in which case stay out of my way
Never expected that from him
Hey, seriously
c'mon you bunch of chickens
They're nuts
Damn it
Alright lets go
Hurry up, follow Mikasa avoid fighting if you can
And get to HQ before you run out of gas
Wow Mikasa is a bad ass
how is she going so fast
No Mikasa is using too much gas
She could run out in any seconds
It doesn't matter how skilled she is
once we loose mobility we are as good as dead
And I see since the fail of the composure
she's letting eternal and destructively grief
At any time, she could
Mikasa
Damn
Jean, you lead the rest to HQ
I'm going after Armin
I'll go with you
Don't be stupid
There is still Titans everywhere
You gotta help the others
It happened
Why this again?
I've lost my family
Why?
Wasn't the first time enough?
It's all over
Nothing left for them to take from me
It's no use
we're not getting anywhere near Headquarters
Unless of course if we don't mind dying
Shit he is out of gas
Stay back
Tom, I'll save you
No wait
I'm coming
Stop it
Why couldn't I stop them?
Why didn't I stop them?
If I kept theirselves together
This never would've happened
I wasn't meant to lead
I'm the last person that should've been given the raids
No
This world is cruel
But it's also...it's also beautiful
It was a good life
Why?
I had already given up
So why?....why am I struggling?
Why..do I keep getting up?
Why am I still fighting?
I mean
I've lost any reason to live
What keeps pushing me?
[Eren]: Fight
Eren
[Eren]: Kill or be killed, the only way to live
[Eren]: Is to fight
I'm so sorry Eren
I have throw giving up
I'll never give up again
Because if I die
These memories of you die with me
That's why I'll do whatever it takes to win
Whatever it takes to live
What was that?
That Titan
He is..
Killing
He is killing the other Titan
Please be alright
I'm coming for you
There she is
Mikasa are you okay?
Are you guys alright?
Yeah
Then we better get out of here
Crap! Two 15 meter Titans
No that one's different
How
It just finished it off
It know exactly where the weak spot was
Come on guys time to split
last thing we need is him coming our way
No he has no reaction to us
Any other Titan would have been on top of us by now
It seemed to understand the skill
of hand-to-hand combat, what is that thing?
Just chalk it up as another abnormal
Hell they're always an unpleasant surprise right?
Forget about it let's just get out of here
Wait a minute hold on
Mikasa's tanks are empty
Huh what are we gonna do? we can't clear HQ without your help
There's only one thing to do
I know there isn't very much left in them
but it's better than your empty ones
Armin
This is our only choice
It would be a complete wast if i keep them, but
Use this gas more sparingly
Everyone's lives are riding on you
What have I done?
I led the attack without any regard for their lives at all
I was even reckless with my own life
I lost track of what you taught me
Oh Eren
I'm so ashamed
Eren
There got it the ODM gear is functional
And I restocked your blades
Just...just leave me this one okay
It's just that...I would rather this be my end
not being eaten alive
Why did you?
Armin
I will not leave you behind
What was he?
Where there anymore like him?
I've never heard of a Titan killing another Titan
no one has
But it struck a chord in me
something so...familiar
So Primary
I bear witness to the manifestation of humanity's rage
A Titan killing a Titan
The ferry site of an in action leaves
the 104 Cadet Corps class completely speechless
However the cadets have much more in store for them