Hey mobtop!
Sir!
What do they call you maggot?
Armin Arlert from Shiganshina sir!
Wow seriously? why would your parents
curse you with such a dumb name?
It was my grandfather sir
[Keith Sadies]: Cadet Arlert, why is it rot like you here?
[Armin]: To help you man may overcome the Titans
[Keith Sadies]: That is delightful to hear
you're gonna be a great light snack for them
Row three about-face front
-what do you call yourself?
-Sir!
My name is Thomas Wagner I'm from the trost district
I can't hear you !
(I'm from Trost sir My-)
Look at him go
The man is a master when it comes
to fresh face recruits
That takes me back
-You!
-Sir, Mina Carolina from Trost
Is a pathetic worm like you
the best Carolina's has to offer?
Sir, I'm afraid that's the case, sir
What's the point of all  the intimidation?
it's a rite of passage
Through stress and integration
we revert them into blank slates
From there we can mold and bit-by-bit into proper soldiers
he is the first step in that process we
We seem to really excelled that back home, sir
Row Four about-face
There's some he's passing by
A drill instructor is nothing compare that
what those recruits have seen
They were their witnesses to the hell
of the Titan attack two years ago
You can read it in their faces
come on let's go
-what do we have over here?
-Jean Kirschtein, sir from the Trost district
And why are you here cadet?
To join the military police, sir the best of the best
That's nice you want to live in the interior do ya?
yes
No one told you to sit recruit
If you can't handle this Kirschtein
forget about joining the military police
What the hell is wrong with your face you smiling idiot
Marco Bott at your service, sir from GA
South side of wall Rose
I am to join the military police
and give life and limit service to the king
Well then, that makes you an idealistic fool and a rube
You want the truth?
The only use the King has
for your life and limbs are as Titan fodder
Hey Q-ball you're up next
Oh me, sir Connie Springer for Rakago village, sir
You have it backwards Connie Springer
That was the first thing you were taught
This Salute represents the resolve in your heart
To fight though spent on
the systematic destruction of our people
Is your heart on your right side?
Hey you there, what're you think you doing?
You're officially on my shitlist
Just who's the hell are you?
Sasha Blouse from Dauper village
Reporting for duty, sir
Sasha Blouse huh?
And what is that you're clutching in your right hand?
A steamed potato it's sat there
in the mess hall begging to be eaten sir
The theft I understand
But here?
Why eat it here of all places ?
It looks quite delicious and it was getting cold
So I gave it shelter in my stomach, sir
why? I can't comprehend
Why would you eat that potato?
Are you asking me why people eat potatoes?
I'm surprised you don't know, sir
Here sir, have half
Have half? really?
Man I thought Sadies was gonna kill potato girl
Know what a hell of a first day
It's funny!
Being told to run to the Sun sets
Didn't seem to bother her nearly as much
As losing meal privileges for the next five days
I think she said that she's from Dauper
If I remember right that's a small
hunting village up in the mountains
-Hey what's?
-That there dropouts
They prefer to work in the fields
But it's only the first day!
That's the way it is,
If you can't handle the pressure you've gotta leave
I can't believe anyone would rather
pull plants than fight!
I know about some of us but you never
mentioned where you were from Eren
The same as Armin from Shiganshina
Oh well that means you saw it
you were there that day
-Quiet
-The colossal one, did you see him?
Yeah, yeah I did
Yeah okay, I saw the big guy
-Whoa seriously?
-Okay exactly how tall was he?
-He stuck his head over the outer wall
-Oh wait, I heard he stepped over the wall completely
-So did I
-That was the rumor in my village too
Yeah he was big but not that big
So what did it look like?
It had a mouth like a corpse and no skin just muscles
And the Armored Titan?
The one that broke through wall Maria?
Is that what they're calling it?
And all the panic it was just another Titan to me
No way so what were they like?
Come on, that's enough questions all right
I'm sure he'd rather not relive
everything he went through
Sorry we didn't mean to-
It's not like
That those stupid Titans
they're really not that big a deal
If we focus on mastering
the Omni-Directional Mobility gear they give us
Then it'sTitan payback time
I've waited years to be trained as a soldier
All of a sudden the reality is sinking in
I'm joining the Scout regiment
Then I'm sending the Titans back to hell
I'm gonna butcher them all!
Hey are you crazy or something?
Not that it's my business but signing up
For reconnaissance is like a death sentence
I guess we'll see or at least I will
you see content hiding in the interior with the MPs
look I'm just speaking honestly here kid
I think it's better than being some loudmouth
braggart tough-guy wannabe pretending
He's not as pissed scared as the rest of us
-Are you trying to pick a fight?
-Stop it you guys
Alright sure, makes no difference to me
Hey I apologize sorry for calling you
names and dismissing your choice of career
Put it there kid what do you say?
Right, yeah I'm sorry as well
Um...Excuse me!
I just wanted-
I mean I've never seen anyone like you before
I'm mean..uh
I'm sorry, you have really beautiful black hair
Thank You
Would you lay off it's no big deal
It's just that you get so worked up
You don't think things through
Again with this? if you insist on worry
worry about how long your hair is
It's gonna catch up with you in a bad way
when we start on the ODMs
Okay fine, I'll cut it
How short should I go do you think?
What the hell !?
leave my clothes alone damn it
What did you wipe on me?
Don't worry just my trust
Finished
It's gotta be!
It's bread!
I'm sorry there isn't more it's all i could take
Hey hang on, you really should drink a little water first
Just what are you two girls up to?
Well...she has been running all day
without any food or water
I see so you're trying to be nice
What's the point of breaking the rulesfor potato girl
That mindless act of kindness
gets you absolutely nowhere
Whatever
Let's just get her to bed already
I'm confused are you being nice?
I'm helping her so that she'll owe me one in the future
I intend to make use of her stupidity
It's aptitude test time so listen up
there is no place for you here of you cannot perform
fail and be shipped to the fields
We're just drilling the fundamentals here
You can still determine a cadet's
knack for it just by watching
Like her completely steady, she inherently
knows what to do and how to make it happen
That's what aptitude is all about
-I'd say we have several capable cadets this year
-And what about this guy?
That's precisely why we run these tests
He proves the drive and dedication
do not always translate into capability
What is your bench about function Yeager
straight yourself up
Why am I ?
How do I work this thing?
This can't be happening
Just remember the basics and you should be fine
No need to try any fancy maneuvers
Just focus on your balance,
Then distribute your weight evenly
Between the belts on your waist and your
legs
Loosen up your stance a little bit
If I could do it I know that you can
Okay a loose stance but balanced
Let's give it a shot Armin
Hey Daz
He was talking big about butchering all the Titans
but he got real quiet after ODM training didn't he?
I guess it's the fields for him tomorrow,
Can't keep wasting food on the useless
Eren
Worrying won't solve a thing
There's still time to get some practice income morning
How pathetic how am I supposed to kill them
if I can't even stand up straight
It might be time to let that dream die
What do you mean?
I think you should give up this attempt to be a soldier
There's a lot more to fighting and combat
than just throwing your life away in vain
What are you saying after everything we saw that day
After what happened to my mom
You're crazy if you think I'm just gonna walk away
I get it
But it doesn't matter how determined you are
Wait what do you mean?
because whether or not you're fit
to be a soldier, isn't up to you
-You misunderstand
(-Let's go)
-I'm not saying you should return to the fields by yourself
I wouldn't dream of it
Because wherever you go I'm gonna go with you
So are you saying that
you are not going to finish that?
What's the trick to posture control?
hard to say guess I got the gift
you've just got to feel it you know
I'm trying to figure out your trick
you've screwed up every way imaginable
Short of an accidental equipment related asphyxiation
Please guys you gotta help me
I'm begging you
That's funny wasn't it just yesterday you said
if you can't handle the pressure you gotta leave?
No wait was it if you're a complete idiot you gotta leave
Something like that
Oh come on,
I heard from everyone you're both really good at it
Bertholdt, Reiner!
Sorry kid but there isn't any special trick to just hanging there
Not to be harsh but if it's advice you
well I'm not really the guy
-All right
-Let's just hope it comes to you tomorrow
Hold on,
Aren't the two of you originally from Sheganshina?
Yeah that's right
Then you should know firsthand how terrifying they are
Why on earth would you want to be soldiers?
I didn't see the things Eren did he saw their bloodlust
firsthand before anyone realized how bad it was
And I
I knew I couldn't sit idly by as
the Royal government forced the citizenry
Into the failed territory retrieval operation
-I see
-So where the two of you from?
oh Reiner and I?
We were both from a mountain village
Just south east of wall Maria
What? then that means
Yeah unlike the more prosperous river towns
Our village didn't receive word right away
The Titans were on us
before we even knew what was going on
It happened at dawn
All the livestock were so Restless
Soon after we heard these strange rumblings
that just became louder and louder
Eventually I realized those rumblings
Were the sound of death getting closer
I
I looked out my window and
After that
Well, everything is just a blur
I think we all just panicked
Hey easy now
You're just getting yourself worked up again
Sorry, basically what I've been trying to say is this
the four of us aren't like the rest of them
-Them who?
-The others here who've never been witness
To the Titan's horror
Hey
Most of them are here for show
to do just what society expects
In a world where you're labeled a coward
if you choose fieldwork
By the time you turn 12
propriety demands our service
With that said I'm really no different from the others
I joined the ranks hoping for assignment
To the military police
Tucked away in the interior
If that doesn't work out I'll give up entirely
I don't really have the fortitude for anything else
There's no shame in caring about your life Bertholdt
We all do
Do we?
I'm going to return to the home that was taken from me
That's all I care about now
I will do it, No matter what what
What about you?
Why did you sign up?
why did I join?
I decided I have to kill them
I won't stop till every
single Titan is dead and rotting
Dead, every last one
You saw what those monsters are capable of
and you still want to take them on?
Damn right, it's just after screwing up the training
I don't know if I'm cut out to be a soldier
We'll take it from step one,
Belt adjustment, by tomorrow you'll be an expert
I know you've got what it takes
I can see in you, Am I wrong here?
No, I won't fail
Thank you Reiner thank you
-Eren Yaeger are you ready?
-Yes sir
I'm going to do it I have to
I may not be as talented as the rest
but nobody, nobody has more guts
Proceed
The moment of truth I won't fail
The hell with working the damn fields
I'm not giving up
Not without a fight
I did it?
No, I'm doing it
No, not yet
Once more, I can do it
[Keith Sadies]: Lower
I, I'm finished
Vogner please exchange belts
with mr.Yeager
Yes, sir
their equipment was defective
If given a piece of functional gear
you might not be worthless after all
What a master didn't notice this broken clasp
Might have to visit the supply depot
and crack a couple skills
He still did it even while wearing that busted gear
Amazing!
So you mean I, I didn't wash out?
You made the cut, now keep training cadet
I did it, I really did it
Check it out Mikasa I'm doing it
I can fight the Titans
You don't have to worry about me
not anymore
It seems like things worked out for him
look his eyes are saying check me out
They're not
His eyes are saying he doesn't have to loose me
Grisha, today should bring you pride
Your son is a soldier
After graduating from the cadets
Eren sees mankind begin to restore it's dignity
We can beat the Titans
The moment he feels certain of this
humanity has given a grim reminder