They first appeared over a hundred years
ago
Giant humanoid creatures with a tease for our blood
The brute strength of these separations
trumped an average person's many times over
We were shoved to the brink of extinction
Almost overnight
The survivors erected walls
Maria, Rose and Sina
Withdrawing behind them and frightened Huddle's
For what was to be a century of uneasy peace
And then
Till then a man apart from god
All wretched was i
having graven in us are powered by avarice
now that I'll beholdest
Am I here punished for it?
Punished by the justice of god
taint
Upon the penat of there rising souls
The mountain holds no greater pain
As greed has grown all of every corner
Every right so justice here doth chain
What else may have any grace doth our sins as us
For when did not our aim to hide between and like th-
[Hannes]: Damn it! stop
[Eren]: You son of a bitch we could've saved her
We almost had her out
Why did you come? why?
I told you to stop
[Mikasa]: Eren!
[Hannes]: Look
There's nothing you could have done
for her you understand?
you're a kid you're weak
I'm worse
when push came to shove
I was too frightened to hold my ground
your mother died
because I'm a damn coward
I'm sorry
[Mikasa]: That's the same thing all over again
Hurry up! keep your eyes at the gate
Drop everything
find the ferry nearest  to you
and climb aboard for all you worth
Move it
These saints aren't gonna give you a head start
so-called outlier districts like Shiganshina
shut out like thorns
At vital spots along wall Maria
Their basic function is to streamline troop dispersal
And keep security costs down
by drawing Titans into specific areas
The calculated design flaw in all outlier districts
Is that they have only a single gate
through which its citizens
Are able to retreat deeper inward
should the need arise
No personal belongings we need to make
as much room as possible oh you best
Armin you best have a seat
I will just keeping an eye out
for my friends
There they are
Eren
I wouldn't try to call out just now
Give them their space
god only knows what they've just seen
Stop dragging you feet
Snap out of it, I need those canons loaded
C'mon they're heading right for us
This isn't real! this is a nightmare
God help us
Hey, what're you doing?
I'm sorry it's at full capacity
You can't do this, please
At least  let our children on board
Look, there is nothing we can do
Push off now
Don't leave us
There is still room
What are you aiming at?
Did you got crushed in your head?
Sir with respect
Through all this aim are not designed
for accuracy, to begin with
You gonna give me attitude
or you gonna reload?
Stop whining and do your job
What is the point
No! the inner gate
I am not getting left behind
wait are you out of your mind
Don't shut it yet we've still got people
out there give them a chance
We can't let the titans get through the inner gate
If that happens the handful of lies out
there will be the least of our problems
There aren't enough resources for the
whole human race
To retreat behind the next wall they break through
Listen to  yourself
We're soldiers we don't get to decide who lives or dies
What are you waiting for?
The Titans are closing the gap that
That doesn't
Bring her down
No
Let go of me
What the hell !
Oh No!
Hurry
Impossible
We've got to get the hell out of here
Retreat
Shut the gate Now!
We're being charged
Help!
Oh God
Bad news travels fast hours after Shiganshina fell
Every man woman and child within the interior
knew the unthinkable had come to pass
Terror spread like wildfire
What do you think we're meant to make of these reports of Shiganshina falling to the Titans
Are they verified that?
That outcropping is held for a century
it makes no sense
Whether or not they're verified
The refugees are certainly
flooding in like plague rats
There have been at least five hundred
accounted for in the boats
The question is
How prepared are we if Shiganshina is in ruins ?
Come now surely while Maria is enough
on its own to hold the Titans at bay
Don't you think ?
Damn it all!
Anyway it's a slice the situation is untenable
Our hands are tied, I say we make Appeals
To the central government for help
excuse me my Lords you really want to
hear this
Wall Maria has been broken through
The Titans are.... they're in
This is the end
That's it we are all dead
We are dead and standing in the gate of hell
It's gone
Our house, it's all gone
Forever
Why was i always such a brat
Why did I always fight her
I never said "I love you"
Now I will never get to
Never
There's nothing you could have done for her
you understand ?
Because I'm a kid, because I'm weak
Because every last one of us is a damn coward
No, this isn't over
[Mikasa]: What are you?
[Armin]: Whats wrong? you see something?
Eren?
I'm gonna put a stop to this
I'll kill them all
Every last one
Eren?
In terrified haste the central government
declared the outlier districts a lost cause
And decreed all mankind retreat behind wall Rose
Estimates held that nearly 10,000 lives
were lost to the titan offensive
[Grisha Yeager]: Eren, Carla, Mikasa
Please be alive
Eren
Stay with me boy, wake up
[Eren]: Stop it, please you're scaring me
I dont understand what are you trying to do
[Grisha]: You don't have to, just give me your arm
[Eren] : No
You're insane, mom's death pushed you off the deep end
[Grisha]: Shut up
[Eren]: No, let me go
[Grisha]: Damn you, this is the only way
[Eren] : You're not making any sense
[Grisha]: You cannot forget the key,
whatever you do you must reach it
It's the way to the truth
One day you'll understand
[Mikasa]: Hey it's okey, you were just dreaming
[Eren]: That was, it felt so real
[Mikasa]: Nightmare shake it off
[Eren]: Yeah
[Mikasa]: come on they're handing out
food rations near the warehouse
I think this used to be
where they stored all the dry goods now
Now it's where they Corral the refugees
I don't think so Friend
give me a break the all I've have for two days
is a molded bread across
How do we exactly a dignified existence
[Armin]: Hey guys
[Eren]: Armin?
I'm glad I caught you
Here grandpa scrambled the little extra
by telling the garrison he had guests
That was nice of him
what's his deal
just ignore it there's a shortage
poor man's probably hungry
By the way I'd make that last
they were already dealing with famine
Before we got here so it's an ugly situation
That and this far in there's a greater
disparity between the haves and the have-nots
Nothing more gratifying than
senior rations go to animals
Guess we got a beef up the herd though
eat up the titans like a little meat on their bones
Eren wait
Ought to keep you in cages
should be out to the front lines as a buffer
damn it you picked the wrong man asshole
Spineless cowards all of you
you don't, know what it's like
You've seen one?
You've seen what they can do?
You little piece of -
He's sorry he didn't mean it
He's just hungry
We all get that ways speak
our minds out of turn sometimes
forgive him I beg you
yeah well keep in mind it's given up
their share so you can eat
in case you hadn't noticed we're all hungry
tell your buddy a little gratitude goes a long way
Sure
Bastard I'm not a prat
to show gratitude to a coward
I can't do this
I'm going back to wall Maria
The Titans have to pay
for what they've done to us
Hey now you're not serious
that's your stomach talking
No it's not
Wake up the guys
standing between us and them
Are just a bunch of talk
The hell with all of them
Here, give it back
Yeah what are you trying to do starve?
When are you gonna get sick of
their charity too much is handed to us
We have to stand on her own two feet
To do what? get killed by a Titan ?
I know I used to think our future
was beyond the walls
But it's like you told that man
I never seen what they could do to us
So that's it this is just the way life is
Run away and take what we were giving
Look at us, what choice do we have here?
you can damn well leave
If you want to scrape by on the charity
of cowards that's your thing
but I'm not a parasite
Mikasa?
Have you looked in the mirror lately?
All of us are parasites
We couldn't run from certain death without help
Tell me differently
Don't take your shortcomings out on him
For God's sake we can't even find food on our own
we're parasites we're cowards
Titans are at the top
of the food chain period
Pride be damned
we do what we must to live
Your mom didn't ask us to be brave
Mikasa?
Eat it she asked us to stay alive
I'm not about to let her down
A few days later
Throngs of starved refugees
Were put to plow in the wastelands
as a last-ditch effort to raise food
But the cold hard ground yielded nothing
And the following year 846
the remaining refugees old enough
To serve in the military
were tasked with reclaiming wall Maria
Of the 250,000 sent
nearly 20% of the surviving population
Not even 200 made it back
While it did nothing to drive back to Titans
Their sacrifice did at least lessen
the effects of famine within the interior
We have to find a way to stop them
Our lives will never be our own until we do
This world will never feel like home
That's it
Next year I'll be applying to join the cadets
To become strong enough to fight back
I'm with you
You don't have to
I do
So do I
Dammit not trying to drag you in
look there's no point in following me to my death
Yeah, and if I can help it
then it won't be your death
All right, together then
Straight those spines pissheads 104
cadet corp boot camp starts now
Allow me to introduce myself
I'm commandant Keith Sardis
And you will gonna hate me
Training is gonna be a white-knuckle
ride through hell
If I've done my job you'll be waking up
in a cold sweat from memories of this place
Every night for the rest of your miserable lives
Right now you're nothing, livestock
But over the next three soul-crushing years
you'll learn to take down your own Goliath
remember this moment
when you come face-to-face with him
Because here's where you ask yourself
Am I a fighter? Or am I feed?
Am I gonna be ground up to pulpy
human grist between both of sides it's incisors?
Or am I gonna be the one to bite?
Oh I'm a fighter alright,
and before I'm done with them
The Titans will grow to hate me
see
you
it isn't easy hard truth passions no
guarantee he'll stick the landing
unless you can transmute it into skill
when you're floored by fundamentals all
the heart in the world means nothing