In the year 845,
two terrifying new breeds of Titans appeared
The Colossal and Armored
Barreling through the outer walls
as if wholesale destruction was child's play
The territory couched within the circle
of wall Maria was abandoned
Twenty percent of the human race
perished
As the Titan onslaught advanced our only choice
was to his draw behind Wall Rose
Five years later in the year 850
[Eren]: Mankind didn't start this fight
but we're gonna finish it
Mount to cannons squad four
Take out the Colossal Titan
This is our chance
Don't let it slip away
You
It's been a while
Son of a bitch !
He took out the cannons
the gate was no accident then
He! he planned it
He has intelligence!
All the more reason not to waste this moment,
without him the other Titans have nothing
I'm gonna take him down
Damn it!
Take this
How did I miss
What the -
Did he just vanish in the thin air?
Eren where did he go ?
Did he get away or did you take him out ?
He's gone exactly like five years ago
He's here one moment and gone the next
Just like that
I'm sorry
Don't apologize, look at us we were too scared to move
Hey wallow on your own time
In case you hadn't noticed there's a breach
we have to act now if they start pouring in that's it
Look alive operation Colossal Titan response is in effect
I expect you to take part report to HQ
If you got close to the damn thing we need details, Sir
sir we pray the advance team will be victorious
Here down, take only what you need to survive
You understand what we're facing
If they get through we'll have a repeat of five years ago
Consider this the last line of defense
The Titans get held up here or nowhere
Prepare to intercept
Fire
SOLDIERS CHARGE
Out of the frying pan and into the fire cadets
Time to put your training to work
I have faith each of you will be a credit to your regimen
I promise we'll get through this
You're safe as long as I'm aside you
Franz...
Armin, what's wrong?
I... don't worry I'm fine
Just give me a second for my nerves to settle
this is bad isn't it
There's a hole in the wall eight meters wide and we don't
even remotely have the engineering know how to plug it
That huge boulder near the front gate was our best bet
but we couldn't figure out how to host it in place
Unless we seal the breach
the entire city isn't gonna stand
How long do you think before they take wall Rose?
Seriously, how long ?
Think about it, anytime the mood
strikes them taking one belt
-The human race in an afternoon
-Armin, listen to me
You're focused on the past look ahead
We're not gonna be the victims anymore
Sorry I...I'm okay
Come now take this seriously
Very well yet another victory is mine
Dear oh dear,
One would think our monthly rose would see at least
Some modest improvement
in your approach to the game Pyxis
One would think so yes clearly
my brain is inferior to yours Lord Falls
Such obsequiousness from the single
highest-ranking officer in the southern territory
Tell me seriously how can you hope to thwart
(Commander Pyxis sir I bring news)
I beg your pardon young man this is-
(The Colossal Titan has laid siege to the city of Trost)
Reports say the gate has been destroyed
Ah this vintage is worthy of your good taste
One man of action to another
I obsequiously accept it as a gift
Where you going Pyxis wait
You can't just march off i command you to stay
Preparations must be made
The symbol of your troop said establish a garrison
around my estate this instant
Damn it all it's your sworn duty to defend us
Lord Walt sir!
Untold numbers of our brave comrades and
arms are laying down their lives
-In defense of trust as we speak
-Commander, I'll go ready the horses sir
When the dust is settled there may well be more graves than people to dig them
-An astronomical number of lives
snuffed out in a twinkling
Yes, well no help for it is there if it's their time
besides what earthly good can the presence of a man
Who persistently loses to me at chess do
for them now why not remain where I can assist you
Your lordship if I may speak freely
Should the commander actually face a Titan in battle
He won't feel compelled to play down his skill
As he does with you
That's enough soldier
Good day sir, I wish you another
opulently appointed day of sloth and tranquility
Please don't go, don't do this to me
Pixis please I'm begging you
Pixis!
I want everyone split into four squadrons as practice
All squadrons are responsible for supply running, message relay and enemy combat
Under the command of the garrison regiment
the intercept squadron will be taking the Vanguard
Cadets will be taking the middle guard
led by the support squad
Rearguard will go to the elite
I expect you all to man your posts
knowing the advance team has been wiped out
That's right the other gate is  history the Titans are in
This means the Armored Titan is likely to reappear
If and when he does the inner gate
will also be history
-Is this real ?
-At least be a dream !
God !, what if the bastions managed
to bust through wall Rose
QUIET!
Right those are the vanguard be ready
The whole areas as well not saturated
your mission is a very simple one
Defend the wall for the evacuation is done
Now be aware all of you
that desertion is punishable by execution
If becomes to it lay down your lives
dismissed
SIR!
Why did this have to happen now?
Just one more day and I'd have been
heading to the interior
[Christa]: You gonna be alright
Please No! Please No! Please No!
Move it
What the hell man? what's wrong with you?
What kind of question is that?
we're all about to be Titan's shit
And you expect me to sing you a happy little solemn
you're loving this aren't you?
you little psycho
Of course you are your whole
life's aspiration is to be eaten
I was one day shy of shipping off to the MP
-Jean get a hold
-No, not all of us are suicidal
-Damn it ! shut up for a second
We're trained for this
what do you think the last three years were about?
We survived we stared death in the face
and we lived, not everyone can say that can they?
Some people couldn't take it
and either ran or were thrown out
Hell some people actually died, but not us
Am i right? we powered through for three years
what's one more day
you can do this Jean alright,
the MP will still be waiting for you tomorrow
Shit
On your feet Daz stop bawling
Okay
Eren if things take a turn for the worse
I want you to come find me alright?
What we're in completely different squads
Look this is gonna get ugly and when it does
the plan goes out the window
Come and find me so I can protect you
who the hell do you think you are you're?
(Ackerman)
You're with me you've been assigned at the rearguard
on special orders let's get moving
But Sir I'm a cadet
I'll slow everyone down (what)
You're not being asked for a self-evaluation here
The mass exodus is falling apart
We need as many elite soldiers as possible to
get things back on track
Sir, with all due resp-
HEY!
You've been given a direct order
pull it together, Now!
This is bigger than the two of us and you know it
We're on the verge extinction here
have some damn perspective
You're right I'm sorry
this whole situation just has me out of my head
Just promise!
Promise me one thing
Whatever happens don't get yourself killed
I had planned on it, thanks
NO! I won't allow myself to get killed
Not until I taste what life is like outside
of these godforsaken walls
But surviving historical documents we have access to
tell us nothing of the Tigers origin
Almost everything about them is obscure
now that isn't to suggest
We're completely ignorant thanks to the
efforts of the Scout regiment
We do know something of their ecology
Whether Titans possess human-like intelligence
is up for debate of course
And today there have been no reports
of high-level communication between them
We do know that Titan physiology is fundamentally different than most organic life
As they lack reproductive organs it's unclear how they reproduce
Apart from this to all appearances their physique
resembles the average human male
We also know their body temperatures run quite high
And baffling though it is their appetite
seems geared exclusively towards human beings
In fact a Titan striding principle
seems to be this appetite
Given that they've subsisted for over a century without
Access to their only source of nourishment however
We surmise that these creatures
do not in fact consume us to live
Let that sink in, Titans aren't motivated
by hunger as such they're simply in it for the kill
But terrifying vitality of these
creatures is beyond scientific dispute
We have only to consider events
of the recent past to see this
Mankind has long possessed canon technology as you're aware
but that alone proved tragically insufficient
Even with their heads blown to bits
the Titans persist
Though there is some variability on this score
a Titan's head usually regenerates within two minutes
(Is that true?)(As it their size wasn't frighting enough)
Excuse me sir are you basically
saying that the Titans are immortal?
No I'm not, there is in fact
one way to ensure death
Strike here!
If the back of their neck takes adequate damage a Titan will not regenerate
This is the chink in the proverbial armor
That as you may have surmised is where
the flush paring blades you see here come in
A good deep strike with one of these
To a Titans weak spot
And the monster has left no time to regenerate
They die and stay dead
Look at it this way Armin
It's a golden opportunity
I mean if we prove our worthless soldiers right here
We'll rise up right through the ranks before long
we could even be leading our own regiment
we could bypass rookie status altogether
Sounds good I'm with you all the way
Now now boys you're not the only ones in your class
save some of the glory for the rest of us
Good luck beating us to the punch a second time Eren
No head starts for you this round
-Is that a challenge ?
-Listen up whoever kills the most Titans
Gets bragging rights
Heh! Better not fudge your scores
(Squadron 34 move out the vanguard needs support)
Right give them hell!
There is so many of them
The vanguards been completely overwhelmed
I don't believe this
those guys always talk so big
I thought things will be hearty
But this? this is insane
We've got an abnormal!
Hold on!
Oh God please help me!
You bastard
-Eren!
-Wait stay with the group
Get back here
you gonna pay for killing my friend
You're not getting away
-Eren
-Oh God no!
Please help i don't want to die
Why?
My friends are being devoured
And all I could do is watch
What's wrong with me
Why can't I move?
No  Armin
[Armin]: Eren! Eren!
[Armin]: Eren!
-Why are you shouting?
-Sorry
I found a book my grandpa keeps hidden away
Believe it or not it's about life on the outside
I really hope this is your idea of a joke
stuff about the outside world is illegal
Seriously you could go to jail for them
Trust me you change your mind if you knew what was actually out there
For example; according to this book most of the world
is covered with salty water so deep
you can't reach the bottom
There's a name for it too they call it the sea
Like salty for real?
c'mon you're making it up
If something valuable like salt
Was just floating around underwater merchants
would have scooped it out ages ago
That's the thing the sea never runs out
It's that big!
Yeah whatever
Just bear with me there's a lot more than salt
Water that glows like fire, fields of ice
Giant rocks that take days to climb
Imagine how huge the outside world must be
It does sounds really neat
Ok you've got to promise on your life not to tell anyone
But my parents are, well they're going to sneak
outside the walls to see for themselves
Don't know what it's like firsthand look at me
We should do it ourselves one day we can have
adventures like the guy who wrote this book
Eren!
I refuse to die like this
Understand?
Armin listen
We still going to the outside world
that things you told me about it
I have to see them
I have to-
Eren! NO!
All of a sudden it's raining the sound
is so faint so gentle
The scent is so light flowers odd now
we can remind you of something so horrible