In the year 850, the Colossal Titan again appeared
and decimated yet another barrier between us and them
Once more, mankind retreated in panic
before the advance of its greatest foe
Brave soul after brave soul perished, eaten alive
Eren, No!
Eren himself fell prey to their hunger
Wow Mikasa is a badass
How is she going so fast?
No, Mikasa is using too much gas
I'll do whatever it takes to win
whatever it takes to live
Just when things seem their darkest for Mikasa
Out of nowhere came the unlikeliest of allies
I Can Hear a Heartbeat
There, got it
The ODM gear is functional and I restocked your blades
Just...just leave me this one okay
It just...I would rather this be my end not
being eaten alive
Why did you?
Armin
I will not leave you behind
What?
I mean Titans are everywhere
you jump and carry me on your back
C'mon lets move
Please don't do this
Its not going to work
Enough people have died on my account
No
Hold on, I've got an idea
What is it then?
Only you two are capable of pulling this off
so it's really your choice
This may sound crazy, but I think he might
be useful
Wow you mean that Titan?
He only attacks his own kind
he seems to have no interest in us
What if we could somehow steer him to HQ
And let him loose on the other Titans
Look we know he's taking at least one than already
We can use him as a weapon
You've got to be kidding,
How the hell you think we supposed to steer that thing?
Something tells me he is fighting on instinct
I'm almost sure if you take down the bear
he is tangling with now, he will go look for others
That will lead him straight to HQ
we're not steering him so much as luring him
I think it'll work i really do
Think? you're asking us to risk our necks
on a stupid gut feeling?
If I'm right about this we can put down
the siege on Head Quarters in one fell swoop
It worth a shot
Huh?
seriously?
Better to a gambling on Armin's gut feeling
than wait around to get slaughtered
If there is a decent shot why not take it?
So basically we're gonna recruit a Titan
Yes, Exactly
We'll look like morons if we screw this up
Yeah but, if don't look how many live we'll stand to save
Where there is a will there is a way
It's still nuts but what the hell
Why couldn't I stop them?
I'm the last person that should've been given
the raids
No, No
This is our chance
We can get the drop on them while they're
occupied,
It's Perfect
Let's go
make a break for HQ
while they all are distracted
We can do this
Hey we run out of
gas we're dead anyway
Give it everything you've got
Jean
You really came through for us there man
we owe you big time
Don't knock it off I'm serious
We're alive because of you
like i said you make a great leader
Peace You with that crap we're not out of
this yet
Damn it
How many of us made it?
How many biased to that crawl over?
How many of my comrades died on my order?
Hold on a second
You guys with the supply team?
Yeah
Jean stop
You cowards you left us out there on our own
People are dead because you get never guts to do your job
The Titans were coming at us from every angle
They're here in our supply room okay
It's your job to deal with it and back us up anyway
Hid that back
Son of a-
There is too many people, they can smell us
Run
Get further in
Where is Mikasa? Have you seen her?
She ran out of gas forget about her she is dead
This is it
This is reality
Of course it is
How deluded was I?
No
No at some level i knew it all along
I mean when you stop and think for a second it's obvious
There is no winning
Not against them
What?
What the? my God
Mikasa you are?
Wow close one I was hurling on fumes
we made it here thought, crazy but we did
You- I..
Am I dreaming this or what?
You sir are genius from now on
as far as I'm concerned your words is law
Check it out, we found an abnormal
who's got a bone to pick with his own kind
And the best part
he couldn't care less about us
That's right you heard me
This big beautiful ass-hole beast is our ticket out of here
You mean like fighting fire with fire?
listen to yourself a Titan not gonna help us
You're out of your mind if you think this gonna work
It' is working
For whatever reason, he is rampaging against them
Stand back and let him do it, trust me you'll see
Either way what choice do we have
Right now that thing is our best chance of survival
Look at it go!
This kind makes the others look like total weaklings
They are not gonna take this building
Not with him at a rampage out there
That's all well and good
what's will keep him from turning on us once he's done?
Guess we'll worry about that when we're safe
Yeah you're right at least he is buying us a little time
Good news
Courtesy of the Military Police
And covered with a layer of dust
Are you absolutely sure buckshot is the way to go?
Seems like we might as well throw spit wads
I mean come on guys...are guns even effective?
I don't know but they bound to be better than nothing
We're looking at seven Titans
in the supply room of the 4-meters tall variety
If we time this perfectly
this much ammo ought to be enough to do the trick
STEP 1: We would lower a group into
the area via a left to get the Titans attention
STEP 2: When the Titans come within range the group
fires in all four directions simultaneously blinding them
Then the hard part, the moment of truth as at war
Before Titans have time to recover seven of us
swoop down from the sealing and strike their vital regions
That's is
That's the plan
It puts all our lives on the line
we screw up we're dead
That's a hell of a risk for one attack
but it's our only chance
Seven people have to slay seven Titans
in one blow at the same time
We gonna need the best of you the seven soldiers most
physically gifted and adapted with their baring blades
You will be the difference between life and death
for the rest of us, I'm sorry that's how it is
[Reiner]: Seem like a sound plan
[Annie]: When you gt right down to it
the risk is the same for everyone
Doesn't really matter who goes
But guys I'm willing to be top doubt of it this
one half big strategy can't be our only option right?
[Marco]: Hey don't be so hard on yourself
Come on with what we are looking at
cuz' for our only option, it's pretty well thought out
If we give it our all we might just pull this off
[Mikasa]: It'll be fine you just have to be confident
You're a better strategist than you give yourself credit for
Huh?
I'm serious that mind saved Eren and me more than once
When did I ever saved you? that's not-
Alright the left is ready to go guns are loaded
to the stocks lets go kill some Titans
You didn't realize it at the time we can talk about it later
Okay I'm gonna ask the obvious question
can we do this without ODM gear?
No Problem these guys are only 4 meters tall
Their weak spots are not too far above eye level
He is right size won't be an issue the spot still
only 1 meter high and 10 centimeters across
Back at the head to the nape at the neck
Worse comes to worst you can always just shove
one of these up their ass that's the other weak spot
Are you serious? that's news to me
Did I miss a day of training or something?
[Jean]: Come on knock it off Reiner
you wants your final words to be an ass jokes?
[Marco]: Good we're still at seven
[Marco]: Okay now nice and easy
Don't lose your cool
fire only when they are all within range
Steady
That's right....wait for it
Our lives are riding on this
Gotta make this attack count
Steady
Almost
Fire
Right, how are you guys?
[Sasha]: I...I'm sorry...I did it
[Connie]: Oh crap
I didn't mean to sneak up on you
Sasha and Connie missed
Need of the hell back
I...oh God
No...I said I'm sorry
Mikasa
You saved my life
Are you okay?
Because of you I am
Then get up
I owe you one
No worries
By the skin of your teeth
You damn lucky you didn't end up worse off
They are all dead
Start loading up supplies
It worked
We gonna make it...we gonna live
No more of them coming in
Thank you crazy berserker Titan
I gaved if went through whole again
I'm never gonna be able to face any of them again
Damn it feel sorry for yourself later focus on escape
[Jean]: Listen now what you said about me being
a leader and all...don't talk about that again right
[Marco]: Promise me you're not gonna take this the wrong way
But I don't think you're a good reader cuz you're strong
I think you're a good leader
cuz you know what it is to be weak
You're one of us you scared out of your mind
just like we all are
It makes you alert sympathetic
You made a damn good call out there
Got me running for my life you're why i can say this
Ready people let's do this
Mikasa?
What're you doing we have to leave now
Look down there
Cannibalism?
And he is not regenerating like the others?
This may sound stupid
but I was hoping he'd be the key for us
That he'd help mankind break the cycle
Turn the tide just long enough
to give us a little ray of hope
[Reiner]: She is right he's too valuable to just let die
There is too much we can learn from it
I think it's perfectly clear our priority
should be to wore the scavengers off
He is no good to us picked apart
[Jean]: Are you out of your mind we've got a bath
out of this nightmare and you want us to stay?
[Annie]: Think about it having an abnormal
as an Allie would be an incredible advantage right?
The cannons got nothing on a Titan
who'd like to strip apart his own kind
You? do you hear yourself?
He is going like a new friend
Oh no
It's the one that ate Tomas
Holly!
What was that you were saying?
Cause I think it's a move point now
Alright enough of this lets leave while we can
We're lucky the ugly bastard didn't get bored
we'd have been the next on the menu
Look Titan is a Titan
Mikasa
It's him
Ah his arm !
It's like...I don't understand
I watched him getting eaten
I watched him die
He is so...
How is this...possible?
Okay, so all the...
Eren did all this?
The overwhelming desire for revenge
An emotion powerful enough to alter
even our physical bodies
When he transforms he went
to the very thing he despises however
You might just find a sort of your allies turned on you