CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
I used to
love Springfield Park,
but it's gotten
so run-down.
(dog howling)
Oh, the "prid" is gone.
Oh, this whole place
is disgusting.
I agree.
Hey! Aren't you that crazy
Cat Lady?
Yes, I am.
But thanks to this
psychoactive medication,
I enjoy brief moments
of lucidity.
Those are just
Reese's Pieces.
-(crazed raving)
-(cats yowling)
I know
how to save this park.
I'm gonna organize
a charity carnival.
Uh, Mom?
Looks like someone
beat you to it.
God, that Junior League
burns me up.
Step right up,
and bid on items donated
by local businesses.
Oh, I've only got
a hundred dollars.
I better bid shrewdly.
First up is this
video camera.
One hundred dollars!
$100 and 50 cents!
Sold!
Damn it!
(groaning)
I never win anything.
Ooh, here's something
I'm good at.
(humming)
(bells and whistles blaring)
(moans cheerfully)
Yes!
Check it out,
Fat-wad!
I'm better than you,
and I'm only ten.
(laughing)
Fat-wad! I love it!
(indistinct talking)
Easy... gentle...
¡Ay caramba!
Mm-hmm.
I'm number one!
I beat my son!
Victory is mine,
so kiss my behind!
(scatting, grunting)
In your face!
♪ My son flips frogs
like a girl! Yeah! ♪
♪ A-boo, a-bah,
a-who's your daddy? ♪
(scatting, grunting)
Hey, Homer, do fries
come with that shake?
Sure do.
Hmm...
(crowd cheering)
(scatting, grunting)
I'm happy!
(cheering)
(Homer laughing)
He makes me look cool.
And cool I am not.
May I upload your footage
onto my Web site?
Well, sir, I don't believe
we've ever met.
My name
is Jeff Albertson,
but everyone calls me
Comic Book Guy.
Well, I'll just
call you friend.
Here's your tape...
friend.
(laser blasts, screaming)
What should we click on next?
Boxer shot by wife.
Beauty pageant diarrhea.
KEARNEY: Here's a new one.
Big-ass Baryshnikov.
(laughing)
Now to send this spaz
around the world.
(snooty laughter)
(laughter)
(amused tongue clicking)
(seals laughing)
Stupid Internet...
whole world laughing at me...
Look at the American
computer monkey!
Dance-a, monkey,
dance!
(bellowing)
Basta, basta.
Take-a my picture
with the Internet marmaluke-a!
(yelling)
(arcade game beeping)
(ape-like grunting)
(bells dinging)
The Internet wasn't
created for mockery.
It was supposed
to help researchers
at different universities
share data sets.
It was.
(doorbell chimes)
Hello,
I'm Deion Overstreet.
The running back
for the San Antonio
Cow Skulls?!
Five-time rushing leader,
two-time MVP
and star of
a Disney Channel movie.
I played the gentle giant,
"Stay-off-drugs-ia."
I know why you're here.
You wanna see me humiliate
myself with my stupid dance.
Well, fine.
(unenthusiastic scatting)
Wrong!
Sidestep,
sidestep, shuffle...
I wanna buy the rights
to that dance for $1,000.
Whoo-hoo! But why?
My workman-like touchdowns
never make
the highlight reel.
But if I add
your shameless shenanigans,
I'll be on ESPN
every night.
You wanna do my dance
after you score?
You damn straight,
and I'll buy
any other dances
you've got, too.
Whoo-hoo!
(cheerful scatting)
(sighs)
(Homer continues scatting)
-(buzzing lips)
-(grunts)
♪ "L" is for "loser" ♪
♪ Which describes you, sir ♪
♪ Don't try to stop me ♪
♪ Just enjoy the view, sir. ♪
"The view, sir."
Then show ass.
Got it.
Honey,
I bet you're wondering
why Daddy's not at work again.
The answer may surprise you.
I have a new job
choreographing end zone dances
for a professional
football player.
Looks like all you're teaching
is obnoxiousness
and poor sportsmanship.
Don't forget showboating.
That's the cornerstone of
my "Pyramid of Success."
Ooh,
I forgot crotch grabbing.
That'll be the sun.
Mm-hmm.
(cheerful music plays)
Grandpa,
will you take me fishin'?
Sorry, Jimmy--
your Grandma and I
are going to go have
old-people sex.
Thank you, Jammitin!
(rock music plays)
Oh, there's nothing
but filth on TV.
But with this
new video camera,
we can make
our own entertainment.
Now boys, we're gonna
film the world's
first and some would say
best murder mystery--
the story of Cain and Abel.
Daddy, if Cain and Abel were
Adam and Eve's only children,
how did they make more babies?
Did they make babies
with their mother?
Or with each other?
Your mouth is hopin'
for a soapin', boy.
Now stop asking silly questions
and go kill your brother!
(whimpers)
After you prance across
the goal line,
you hurl the other team's
mascot to the ground
and drive your cleats
into his neck.
(crowd cheering)
You're going down,
you potato-eatin' pansy!
Homer, are you sure we aren't
crossing a line here?
I happen to know
that the person
inside that leprechaun suit
is a single mother.
Deion,
this is Timmy Thomas.
(whispering):
He has Timmy Thomas disease.
Mr. Overstweet, could you do
an obnoxious end zone dance
for me today?
(coughs)
Pweeease?
Yay!
♪ Everybody dance now ♪
(dance music plays)
♪ Give me the music ♪
♪ Everybody dance now ♪
(chewing)
(creaking)
How you like me now?
(whistle blows)
(cell phone ringing)
Yello.
Homer, this is LeBron James.
The fans love my dunks,
but they hate my dancing.
(crowd booing)
I think I can fit
you in.
Let's see...
Lenny, can I move you
from Wednesday at noon
to Sunday at 6:00?
Homer, you know
that's when I play
with neighborhood dogs.
All right, all right,
I'll work it out.
Aw, you guys are
what it's all about.
Reverend, thanks
for turning the church
into a "He-without-cineplex."
What the...Oh, I get it.
Boys, I just
talked to God.
He's vacuuming Heaven
to get it ready
for when dead people
show up,
and He'd like you both
to render a sacrifice.
I shall sacrifice
my finest grains
and livestock.
(flies buzzing)
Behold,
I have found favor
with the Lord.
So shall my knife
find favor with thy belly!
(grunting)
(laughing maniacally)
(groans)
Now I must bury my son,
while you wander
the earth forever
with the mark of evil
upon your face.
(viewers gasping)
(cheering)
(groans)
Ned, your film
was a masterpiece.
It turned me
from an atheist
to a hurray-theist!
Sir, you have revealed
to me a world of faith,
beyond the world of science.
I would pay to see it again
and again and again and again,
but not six times.
I also would pay
to see it again.
Me, too.
Here's some guy's wallet.
I am that guy!
Smithers,
we could make a fortune
with these Bible pictures.
And I've been looking
for a way to launder
the money I made selling
club soda as flu vaccine.
Everyone seemed so happy,
but I'm surprised at Ned.
He left out all the good times
Cain and Abel had
when they were growing up.
He's just being true
to the Bible,
which is pretty violent.
And sexy.
King David stole
someone else's wife,
Mary Magdalene was a hooker...
Bart. How do you know
these things?
It's all in this book.
(chuckling)
(groans)
HOMER: Welcome
to the Homer Simpson
Showboating Academy.
Today we're working
on poor sportsmanship.
First, I want you to hurl a ball
at the nearest authority figure.
Nicely done.
Oh, my God!
It's my hero, Michelle Kwan!
You remind me
of a young Dorothy Hamill.
(gasps)
I didn't know you could talk!
Lisa, could you pass
the salad?
And it's James with the steal!
(glass shattering)
(groans)
Who wants to help me
clear the table?
(speaking Chinese)
Wait a second.
I've read that you speak
excellent English.
Shut up, kid.
I got a good thing
going here.
Oh, my.
Ned's next movie seems
even bloodier
than the last one.
Now, there's no need
to actually whip him.
We can put
the sound in later.
No!
As your financial backer,
I insist upon reality.
Pharaoh didn't put
the sound in later.
But who'd know
the difference?
The people being whipped!
(shouting)
(grunting)
Hey, Lovejoy,
you could take a lesson
from Flanders--
you know, inject your services
with a little razzle-dazzle.
Oh, I already do,
if by "razzle"
you mean "piety"
and by "dazzle" you mean
"Scriptural accuracy."
What a tool.
I'm richer than you!
Look out, Jonah!
It's a whale!
Jonah, Jonah...
Jonah!
Arr!
The only just solution
is to cut the baby in half.
Wait a minute.
I killed a baby.
I'm a monster!
I can't take any more!
Ned, there's more to the Bible
than blood and gore.
Oh, I-I guess
you'd rather see a film
about a liberal
European wizard school
or the latest sexcapade
of Miss Ashley Judd.
Well, I don't like
this movie,
and I'm going to boycott
your financier,
Mr. Burns.
Oh, really?
And what will you use
instead of nuclear power?
Solar.
Hydroelectric.
A mix of conservation
and wind.
Who told you about those?
A talking tree
in a commercial.
(sighs): Well, I know
when I've been licked.
Sorry, Ned.
This movie will never
be seen again.
Dis-embroider
the crew jackets.
We can still
send them back.
Mm-hmm.
Welcome to Jock Center!
Tonight, the Clipper
and the Stripper,
a Jones that's Chipper,
and did Joe Torre
shoot Flipper?
But first, professional
sports continues
its downward
march into the gutter.
(chuckling)
This is either about me
or steroids.
Thanks to professional
jerk-ass Homer Simpson,
athletes are now taunting
and boasting just to get
on our highlight reel.
Disgusting.
Now, here's our
highlight reel!
♪
Art comes from pain.
Your pain.
Beware the wrath of Kwan!
TOM:
Everyone sucks but me!
Oh, yeah, cheer for Tom.
Give all your love to Tom.
(chuckling)
I'm the worst thing
to happen to sports since Fox.
Master,
you are truly a fool.
Homer Simpson, we work
for the Commissioner of
Football,
and he wants to see you.
I want to see him, too.
Maybe he can tell me
how to get this off.
It soaked through
to the other side.
MAN: The commissioner's in here
with all the owners.
Homer,
we think you're fabulous.
Since the players began
your rowdy rump-shaking,
our ratings are up 62%.
Plus, we're making millions
in player fines,
which I'm going to use
to bankroll a musical
about The J. Geils Band!
(cheering)
That's right, J. Geils!
Here's why we called
you in:
we want you to produce
this year's Super Bowl
Halftime Show.
Wow. At last, my pathetic
little life has a meaning.
(giggles):
You suckers!
I would've done it for free!
Fine, do it for free.
Damn it!
Well, I'll still do it.
(chuckles): Suckers.
I would've paid you.
Fine, pay us.
Oh, damn it!
Will you take a check?
No!
Damn it!
Mm-hmm.
MALE ANNOUNCER:
The Super Bowl Halftime Show.
From its humble origins
in Super Bowl I...
(playing)
...to the marriage of PacMan
and Ms. PacMan
in Super Bowl XVI...
I now pronounce you
PacMan and wife.
♪ Let's get
physical, physical ♪
♪ I wanna get physical ♪
♪ Let's get physical... ♪
Oh, every single Super Bowl
Halftime Show has been great.
Oh, Homie, don't worry.
I'm sure you'll come up
with a great idea.
I don't know.
It's a lot of pressure.
(laughing nervously)
Do many people watch
the Super Bowl?
-Billions!
-Oh.
(strumming)
(elephant trumpets)
We're ready for rehearsal,
Mr. Simpson.
So, what do we do?
Uh...
Oh, man, I have no idea
what I'm doing.
I wonder if other Super Bowl
producers waited
till 3:00 in the morning
the night before
to plan their halftime shows.
-(tires screeching)
-A church!
Maybe the homeless people
sleeping on the floor
will have some ideas.
Flanders?
Well, I guess you've got
some late night problems,
too.
Yeah.
I made a great film,
but I'm having trouble
getting it out there.
I'm like Michael Moore,
except I'm skinny,
my jeans are washed,
and God loves me.
(sighs): I just wish
I could find some way
to spread my message.
Have you tried checking
the oil filter?
Are you even
listening to me?!
Sure, I'd be happy
to tell you my problem.
I've got a venue
the whole world will be
watching,
and nothing to fill it with.
Wait a minute.
You've got a medium,
and I've got a message.
Maybe God brought us together
for a reason.
Yeah. You help me, and I,
in turn, am helped by you.
ANNOUNCER: And so,
ladies and gentlemen,
we have come to the start
of Super Bowl XXXIX!
This brand-new $300 million
stadium was completed
just one short week ago,
and it's scheduled
for demolition
early next month.
America's priorities
are a joke.
Now, here's the kickoff!
Wow, all these people
are going to see Dad's show.
Oh, I paid a thousand dollars
for this seat,
and I can't even
see the game!
Just poke through.
ANNOUNCER: And that's the gun.
We head into halftime with
the thrilling score of 55 to 6.
But don't stop watching.
In the second half,
points count double.
And now the eagerly
awaited Super Bowl
Halftime Show sponsored
by the new Ford pickups,
Citibank and Moe's Tavern.
How could you afford this?
I hustled a lot of pool.
Uh, hey,
you want to play?
I got to warn you,
I ain't that good.
-(chuckles)
-All right...
Sucker.
(groans)
Who's the sucker now,
huh?
Time for Homer's
halftime show.
Get ready, Frank.
Frank went to the men's room.
I'm Joe.
HOMER (over P.A.):
We now take you back
through the ages
to a time before TV,
before cowboys,
before dinosaurs:
the time of the Bible.
The children of God once lived
according to their
Father's laws,
but then a shadow of wickedness
fell across the land,
as represented by this cloud
of white pesticide.
(coughing)
But there was one
righteous man:
Noah.
O, mighty God, send a flood
to destroy this wickedness!
Hey, do you guys think
Homer's mad at me?
I waved at him
in the parking lot,
and he stared
right through me.
I left the People's Republic
for this?
Yo, Michelle,
you got a boyfriend?
Not in here, I don't.
After 40 days and 40 nights,
the rains stopped,
and Noah sent forth
a single dove...
(whimpering)
(barks)
"So God blessed Noah
and his sons and said to them,
'Never again shall there be
a flood to destroy the Earth.
I set My rainbow in the cloud,
and it shall be a sign
of the covenant
between God and man.'"
Thank you.
(booing)
All over America today,
viewers were outraged
by the Super Bowl
Halftime Show's blatant display
of religion and decency.
You try to raise your kids
as secular humanists,
but these showbiz types
keep shoving religion
down our throats!
Mommy, why wasn't
I baptized?
You see? You see?
I thought America
was hungry for meaning.
I should've just sent
a crocodile into space
like I originally planned.
(groans)
Homie,
I think you did great,
and to celebrate,
I made omelets
from the eggs people
threw at our house.
Dig in, everybody.
Omelets for dinner?
This is the best day
of my life.
Really?
Didn't you just sign
a $90 million contract?
That was a good day, too.
HOMER: Welcome
to the Homer Simpson
Showboating Academy.
Today, we're working
on poor sportsmanship.
But I like to stand
for good sportsmanship.
Quiet, you.
Yes, sir.
Shh!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem