CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(playing the blues)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
BART: Come on, boy.
Take your pill.
(Santa's Little Helper groans)
(gasping, coughing)
Mom, the dog won't
take his medicine.
It helps if you wrap it
in a slice of cheese.
Whoo-hoo!
Free cheese!
Homer, that was for the dog.
What happened
to us, Marge?
We used to feed
each other cheese
and laugh all night.
Then came
the heart attacks.
(rumbling)
What's that rumble?
LISA:
It's a media circus.
Whoo-hoo!
The circus!
A media circus.
Whoo-hoo!
I don't know the difference!
LISA:
ABC, CBS...
Uh-oh, the Christian Science
Monitor has a flat tire.
I'll get the spare.
No. We must wait
for God to jack us.
BROCKMAN:
In Springfield today,
a sex scandal
has brought in reporters
from around the world.
Why, here's Fox News.
♪ We are the champions,
my friends ♪
The cause of all this commotion
is Mayor and suspected
illegal immigrant Joe Quimby,
named today in paternity suits
by 27 different women.
(reporters yelling)
Joe, why won't you
acknowledge our love child?!
Er, uh...
that is not my baby.
Er, ah, waaah.
Raise this as your own.
This is the most
exciting scandal
since the Juice
was on the loose.
The Juice is still
on the loose.
(screams)
Mr. Mayor, just how many
illegitimate children
are you hiding?
Kent, I'm hiding nothing...
except this puppy.
Aww...
Look into his eyes
and tell me I'm lying.
Well, I'm placated,
and so are all my friends
in the local media.
I have a question.
Chloe Talbot,
Global News Network.
Oh, it seems
a big shot reporter
from some major news
outlet isn't satisfied.
Well, if it isn't local
news legend Kent Brockman.
Hey, Kent, run over
any more pedestrians?
Those records are sealed.
She's from Springfield.
I knew her in high school.
I didn't think anyone successful
came from Springfield.
What about that
two-headed goat?
Technically, he was born
in Shelbyville.
Yes, but he came here to die.
One of you ate tin cans,
one of you ate health food.
How you solved crimes,
I'll never know.
Mr. Mayor, you claim to be
faithful to your wife,
but I have obtained
this exclusive video tape.
(muttering nervously)
Come on, baby,
read my sash.
You're the major?
That's mayor,
you fertile moron.
Two things are certain--
the mayor is in deep trouble,
and the local newsmen
in this town are idiots.
Channel Six News rocks.
A car chase every night
or the weather girl
wears a tube top.
And if she doesn't,
you win a pizza.
Chloe sure turned out
successful.
You're successful,
too, Mom.
You made a chore wheel
that's both fair and wise.
(giggling)
Marge, I figured out a way
we can get in
on this Quimby lawsuit.
Bart, go ahead.
(imitates Quimby):
Mayor Quimby is my,
er, uh, father.
Give me one million dollars.
Eh? Eh?
(sighs heavily)
(chanting):
Diamond Joe's got to go!
(chanting continues)
Mr. Mayor, will you answer
one question?
Only if it is submitted
in writing.
Checkmate.
Marge?
Marge Simpson?
Chloe, hi.
Marge! Oh, where
are you living now?
Evergreen Terrace.
Paris?
Just like you always dreamed.
Terrace.
Evergreen Terrace.
The street that
smells like pee.
This is my daughter,
Lisa.
Chloe, I really admire
how you got out of Springfield
and became such a success.
Hey, only the lame-os stay.
And your mother.
Super lady.
(groans)
Well, it is good
to see you, Chloe.
Would you like to come over
for dinner tomorrow?
Oh, I'd love to.
I'm getting so sick of
these greasy catered meals.
You insult me,
you insult Italy.
Which is shaped like a boot.
Who knew?
(doorbell rings)
Homer Simpson.
I sawed you
on the television.
I remember you
from high school.
You barfed in my tuba.
I believe it was
the school's tuba.
Chloe, these kebabs you made
are as good or better
than anything I've ever had
at this table.
Homer.
Oh, Marge,
I'm just being polite.
Hmm.
My back pain's completely cured.
That was one too many.
I got the recipe for these
in Istanbul.
More.
(gobbling)
I was writing a story
for Harper's Magazine.
Harper's Magazine?
I have a picture
of Lewis Lapham on my binder.
(growls)
Oh, but I've been yapping
about myself all night.
Marge, what's exciting
in your life lately?
Well...
Oh. We finally found out
why the dog was scooting around
on his butt all day.
Turns out he had an
impacted anal gland.
The excitement
never stops.
Chloe, would you like
to see slides of our trip
to Athens...
Boulevard
Recreational Center?
I'd love to...
Ooh, my show's on.
Mind if we watch a little?
I guess.
ANNOUNCER:
The Talbot Report
with Chloe Talbot.
Tonight,
Chloe interviews Bob Dylan.
So Bob, what religion
are you converting to now?
Well, I'll tell you one thing...
(incomprehensible rambling)
...shalom.
Followed by Chloe's
triumphant return
to her depressing little
hometown: Springfield.
Hello, Ned.
Hey, Comic Book Guy,
Krusty the Clown...
I thought he was dead.
Yeah? I guess you ain't been
to too many
supermarket openings lately.
(groans)
You know, Chloe, some of us
stayed in this town
and made it a better place.
Oh, come on, Marge.
The only reason we don't
move out of this dunghill
is because of my court-
ordered ankle bracelet.
(beeping)
I'm here! I'm here!
Quit buggin' me.
Why do you always have
to show that to company?
It's a conversation starter.
(beeping)
(groans)
This is the dance
the Chinese government
makes dissidents perform
before they shoot them.
(singing atonal melody)
(imitates atonal melody)
Homer, what are you doing?
I swallowed a chicken bone.
(gagging atonal melody)
(coughs)
Oh...!
Chloe, you've lived so many
fascinating places.
Yes, but down deep in my heart,
I'll always be the girl
who wanted to leave Springfield.
Gee, with all that travel,
you probably haven't
had much time
to find that
special someone.
Oh, I've had a few flings.
(coughs):
Bill Clinton.
Schwarzenegger.
Oh, excuse me.
But not all of us can be
as lucky as you, Marge.
Homer's a wonderful man.
(singing atonal melody)
Did you just swallow
another bone?
Same one.
Chloe is amazing.
Even her serving bowl
smells glamorous.
(sniffs)
That's ridiculous.
No one's bowl smells...
(sniffs)
It's like Christmas in Aspen.
(sighs deeply)
Did you know back
in high school
that she'd be such a star?
Back then,
we were both stars...
in the thrill-a-minute world
of high school journalism.
Together we broke the biggest
story of the semester.
One of the cafeteria workers
was spitting in the soup.
I'll teach you to give me
my first job out of prison.
When we published the story,
we received the school's
highest award.
Ladies, it is my great
pleasure to award you
these certificates of merit.
In this box marked "honoree,"
fill in your names.
And over here,
write in what you did.
I'll be back.
You ain't tasted
the last of my spit.
Oh, that Moe.
But good for you, Mom!
Why didn't you follow Chloe
into journalism?
Well, we both faced
a tough decision...
...go off to journalism school,
or stay in Springfield
with our sweethearts.
(both cooing, murmuring
and smooching)
Stay with me, Marge,
and I promise
we'll travel the world...
and perhaps outer space.
(imitates flying saucer)
(imitates ray gun)
(imitates science fiction
sound effects)
(guttural moans)
(moans and titters)
I love you, Chloe...
and I love you too,
brake fluid.
(belches)
Chloe left town
as soon as Barney proposed.
I would've followed her,
but my plans changed
when God brought me
a wonderful little boy...
Bart, stop that!
This isn't what it looks like.
(muttering softly)
Why would Homer write
his name in grime?
(grunts)
Ah, that's better.
Mom, Chloe just won
the Peabody Award!
Well, I just made the bathroom
floor smell like lemons.
Where's the award for that?
Oh, Mom, don't feel bad.
Everybody
appreciates your...
Uh-oh, I'm late
for my dinner...
with Chloe!
(chuckles)
HOMER:
Good news, Marge!
I've learned to walk
naked on stilts!
-(grumbles softly)
-Oh...
(gasps)
There's Dan Rather
and Tom Brokaw
hanging out
with Kent Brockman!
You want your mic back,
local anchor?
This just in...
I'm pissed off!
Hi, fellas!
Chloe, wanna
feel my muscle?
Chloe has such
an amazing life.
(sighs)
I wonder what would
have happened
if I'd stuck with journalism.
Oh, honey, her life
can't compare to yours.
You've got three kids,
a TV tray from Expo '67,
and you're married
to King Stink!
Yeah, I guess.
Marge, listen to me.
Chloe may have a flashy job,
but you're the backbone
of this family.
You're like the
electrical tape
that holds the two halves
of my car together.
That's a sweet
thought, Homie.
I just hate to see
you upset, honey.
You know what would be
a good name for Maggie?
Chloe!
Oh!
That was such
an exciting night.
Morley Safer
has the biggest head
I've ever seen.
I really had fun.
Oh, it's gonna be a let-down
going to school tomorrow.
We have to make
a pilgrim out of felt.
Hey, I'm covering the U.N.
Women's Conference
in Capital City tomorrow.
You want to come with me?
Oh! That'd be wonderful!
Oh, I'd... I'd have
to ask my Mom.
Well, you can
ask her right now.
She's glaring at us
from the front lawn.
Marge, it's my fault
we're a little late.
How dare you
show my daughter
a life of fun
and possibility?
Hey!
Keep your dish-washing
hands off the Armani!
For your information,
our electric dishwasher
is on the fritz.
Not that you care
about the ups and downs
of my appliances.
Do ya? Huh, do ya?
Oh! That's it!
I'm going to show you
some moves I learned
from G. Gordon Liddy!
I'm so sick of names!
(both grunting)
(yowling and grunting)
Ladies!
(chuckles)
There is no need
to fight over me.
No one's fighting over you!
Oh. Well, then, carry on.
CHLOE: You don't know
when to quit!
"Shiner-Be-Gone."
♪ Too-ra-loo-ra-loo-ral ♪
♪ Too-ra-loo-ra-li... ♪
Hmm.
Lisa, honey,
let me explain
what happened tonight.
Sometimes when your mom
has half a glass of wine,
she goes cuckoo bananas.
Hmm.
So is it okay
if I go to the women's
conference with Chloe?
Let me think about it.
No.
(laughs)
I've never disobeyed Mom before.
Is this a step
I'm really willing to take?
I don't know.
The more I think about it...
Thinking is for losers!
Bart!
Thanks for helping me
make up my mind.
Thanks for cushioning my fall.
I didn't cushion your...
(grunts)
Chloe!
I saw your report
on Kuala Lumpur.
Truly hard-hitting.
Thanks, Tom.
I really appreciate that.
So, I, you know,
I was wondering...
Yes?
Would you like to come
to my celebrity
racquetball tournament?
I'll have to check
my schedule.
(grunts)
(Lisa grunts)
I'll give you
a first-round bye.
Gotta go, Tom.
I'll think about it.
Lisa, breakfast!
I know you're mad at me,
but I hope you're not mad
at Cap'n Crunch.
(gasps)
(grunting)
(gasping)
Homer, we've
gotta get Lisa!
All right.
While I'm gone, boy,
you think about what you did.
Ugh. What did I do?
You, uh...
-Why, you little...!
-(grunts)
Need a reason
for strangling, do ya?
I'll fix your wagon!
(grunting)
-(phone rings)
-Hello.
Chloe, forget about
the women's conference!
I need you to get over
to Mount Springfield.
It's about to erupt!
Don't we have a reporter
who specializes
in natural disasters?
Yeah, he's busy covering
Julia Roberts' last haircut.
(chuckles)
But seriously, he's dead.
Now get going!
Hey, there!
The name's Chet.
I'm your cameraman
for this here 'cano story.
Let's see.
I've been to Afghanistan,
Serbia, Lebanon...
Okay, okay, I lied.
I shoot wedding videos
in Dallas-Fort Worth.
Okay, okay.
Just Fort Worth!
(gasps)
Hello, U.N.
Women's Conference!
Wha...?!
We're trapped!
Lisa, we may not make it,
but at least we can go out
as the great journalists we are.
I'm not a journalist!
You are now.
Remember to keep my boobs
in the shot.
And we're on
in five, four, three...
I don't see Lisa
in any of the seminars.
And I'm growing ashamed
of my penis.
(gasps):
Homer, look!
I'm here at the long-dormant
Springfield Volcano,
which is now spewing noxious
debris into the air.
How male.
(all muttering agreement)
With me is my eight-year-old
camera girl, Lisa Simpson.
She's taken my daughter
to an erupting volcano?
That's it!
She is off
the Christmas card list.
Marge,
that's crazy talk.
Now look.
I'll save Lisa.
Your place is here
with the women.
ALL:
Boo!
Okay, you go save Lisa.
I'll stay here
with the women.
ALL:
Boo!
What do women want?!
(whimpers)
We've gotta go now!
Okay. I'll run
as fast as I can,
but I'm full
of potato salad.
(groans)
I'm sorry, folks.
You're not allowed
to go up there.
In fact, I don't
even know why I'm here.
This lava is
not a criminal.
It hasn't hurt anybody.
(man screaming)
Anybody I know.
Chief, my daughter's
up there.
You're a father, too.
Yeah, but I'm
a cop first...
then a boat enthusiast...
amateur historian...
yo-yo dieter...
then I'm a cop again...
LISA:
Help! Help!
So much
sulfur dioxide!
I'm coming, sweetheart!
(tires squeal)
I'll save you, Lisa!
-(rumbling)
-Oh, my God!
Whoa!
Whoo...!
Be careful, Mom!
There's hot lava
under the ground!
Actually,
when it's underground,
lava is called magma.
You're so smart,
Chloe!
Walter Cronkite told me
the same thing.
Shut up!
(grunting)
Mom, that was
incredible!
Nothing's more powerful
than a mother's love.
Mom, your hair!
Don't worry.
We've got two hours
before it burns down
to my head.
Our top story tonight:
I'm about to die!
Barney,
you saved my life.
Chloe, when you left me,
I was devastated.
But I sobered up
long enough
to become a pilot.
With you beside me,
I think I could
make it work.
How 'bout a half hour
of pity sex?
Is there
any other kind?
(belches)
KENT BROCKMAN:
In the wake of
the devastating eruption,
one Springfielder proved
herself a hero: Marge Simpson.
She's won herself
a free hero...
sandwich at Springfield
Sub Shops.
Extra charge
for warm-ups!
Mom, I wanna be just like you.
I mean the lava part,
not saving Lisa.
Pretend to care!
Well, looking
at you kids,
I know I made
the right choice in life.
I'm sure you did.
But still,
don't you ever wonder
what might have happened if
things had gone differently?
Well...
This is Marge Simpson
reporting from Lake Placid
where the miracle on ice
never happened.
No!
(grunting)
Lisa, what are you doing
in there?
Praying to Buddha,
Jesus, SpongeBob.
There's no time
to be picky.
Perhaps we should help.
Screw her!
(laughs crazily)
Shh!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem