CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(yells)
(jazz playing)
Now, before we eat,
let's remember
what we're celebrating today--
after many years
of hard work,
your father finally
paid off the mortgage.
See you in Hell, document.
ALL: Yay.
All right, Dad!
Way to build equity!
Now remember
to eat smart, people.
Go for the fancy foods--
don't let 'em fill you up
with that cheap stuff.
A roll, sir?
Screw you.
Oatmeal?
(gasps)
Smoked salmon... shrimp...
crab legs.
(grunts)
(gasps)
(grunting and gasping)
(pained laugh)
I win.
Thinner... thinner...
thinner... thinner...
too thin.
Better luck next time,
"Tommy-- Virginia Beach."
(chuckles)
(sing-song voice):
You ate meat.
You ate fruit.
(gagging)
(both grunting)
Stow it, you two.
Ow!
(laughing)
Stop making a scene!
How rude.
What do I have to do
to enjoy a Sunday brunch
with my secret
other family?
I've never been
so embarrassed.
And the worst part is,
this is brunch,
so you've ruined two meals.
I'll see you
all at "lupper."
Why did I ever have kids?
I could have written
symphonies, or been Shakespeare.
(moans)
Here, Homer.
Have a big, frosty mug
of Fuhgetaboutit.
(door creaks)
I wouldn't drink that.
From the looks of this place,
it might kill you.
Oh, who are you,
the health inspector?
Yes.
(all screaming)
(loud belch)
My God, look at this filth.
I ought to close this
dump down for good.
-Huh?
-Wha...?
But then where would I go
to get away from my wife?
Come here, Moe,
you beautiful, hideous troll.
(both laughing)
Guys, this is Frankie
from the Health Department.
We go way back.
Lenny, you don't have
to hide that rat.
Off you go, little fella.
(squeaking)
When we were kids,
our dads used to get drunk
and make us fight each other.
Huh? Huh?
My pop would buy me a malted
for every tooth of Moe's
I knocked out.
That time you blinded me,
he gave you a bike.
That sure was
a good-soundin' bike...
(laughs)
Well, now to give this place
a "thorough inspection."
(clears throat)
Free from infestation?
Check.
Sanitary utensils?
Food hygienically stored?
Only one way to find out.
(gagging and groaning)
(shudders)
Oh my God, he's dead.
Okay, which one
of you guys parked
in front of the hydrant?
Uh, look, I didn't see
nothin' here, okay?
(nervous chuckle)
Just a bunch of
innocent guys,
sitting around,
none of them dead.
Buy yourselves a nice dinner.
(tires squealing)
Uh-huh...
Oh.
So, uh, Mr. New Guy,
what do you think?
Is everything...
hunky-dory there?
Mr. Szyslak,
your tavern
is rife with health code
violations.
You gotta be kidding me.
Like what?
For starters,
the body of my predecessor
is still on the floor.
Oh, yeah.
Uh, well, ya see, trash day
ain't till Wednesday,
so...
(awkward laugh)
Mm-hmm.
Chicken skins in soap
dispenser...
cigarette butts in the air...
toilet on the roof...
I'm shutting you down
till you fix these violations.
Oh, man, I can't afford
to fix all that stuff.
Aw, nuts.
If anybody needs me,
I'll be in the john.
♪ Oh, Danny boy ♪
♪ The pipes, the pipes
are calling ♪
♪ From glen to glen ♪
♪ And down the mountainside ♪
♪ The summer's gone
and all the roses falling ♪
♪ 'Tis you,
'tis you must go ♪
♪ And I must bide. ♪
Moe's, a tribute.
"M" is for Moe,
the owner of Moe's.
"O" is for the "O"
in the middle of Moe's.
"E" is for acceptance.
The feeling I always got here
at Moe's.
(sobbing):
Oh, Moe!
Don't let them
close you down.
It's too late.
I don't have the cash
to clean up the bar.
From now on,
you guys are just
going to have to do
your drinking across
the street.
(pounding dance music plays)
♪ Can't get you out
of my head... ♪
Hey, a beer's a beer.
(grunts)
Oh, I can't go
to a gay bar--
I'm too fat.
Moe, I'm going to help you
reopen your bar,
no matter what it takes.
Mr. Simpson,
for a loan this big,
you'll have to put up
your house as collateral.
Put up my house?
But I just paid it off.
What would Marge say?
Do whatever you have to do
to save Moe's.
I love my Homie.
Okay, honey, I'll do it.
What's going on here?
Nothing. Nothing.
Thanks, Homer.
No one's ever trusted me
before--
except for that one guy
who shouldn't have.
-That was me.
-Oh, yeah.
Homer, those kookoo-birds
at the bank goofed up
and sent us a mortgage
statement.
Marge! How dare you open
a letter addressed
to both of us!
M631700000642J?
This is a new loan
tracking number.
You got a new mortgage?
I had to.
Or Moe's would stay
closed forever.
You gave the money to Moe?
How's he going
to pay us back?
Look, look.
I can see you're upset.
If you need me,
I'll be at Moe's.
Well, maybe I'll go
to Moe's, too,
seeing as I'm now part owner.
Marge, you can't go
with me to Moe's.
I mean,
how would you like it
if I came with you
to your mother's?
I would like it.
You never come
to my mother's.
That's because I hate her.
(groans)
Until you pay us back,
you're answering to me.
And there's going
to be big changes.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
now wait just a minute.
One thing Moe Szyslak
has never had is a partner.
Nor a wife, a friend,
a chum, a casual acquaintance,
a pen pal, a parrot,
a meaningful conversation,
a brief hug or eye contact.
I'm just going to call
the suicide hotline now.
(two electronic tones)
And they've blocked
my number.
Oh, God!
(sobs)
(tires screeching)
(relieved sigh)
Just made it!
(whistle blowing)
Quittin' time!
(tires screeching)
(chuckling)
Boy, I can't wait
to get my lips
around an ice cold...
Marge?
I'm here protecting
our investment.
I'd like you to go home
and make dinner for the kids.
But I don't wanna
take care of the kids.
Uh, um...
How many cigars
are they allowed to have?
Bart sleeps in the microwave,
right?
Quit playing dumb.
How many magic beans
should I sell the baby for?
Three?
Duh, der, duh.
That's me, jerk-ass Homer.
Come on, go home.
(groans)
MARGE: Maybe some cheerier
paint would make this
place less of a dive.
Marge, my customers
don't like themselves.
Therefore, they seek
the darkness.
(moaning)
Well... as fabulous
as your regulars are,
a remodel might bring in
a higher class of lush.
Look, I like Moe's
the way it is, all right?
And I ain't changin' it
for any dame, skirt,
Susie-Q or face-macer.
I had a feeling
you'd say that,
so I prepared something
that might help you
change your tune.
(dramatic show tune plays)
♪ This place is a diamond,
but it's trapped in the rough ♪
♪ Yeah, well, the sign
still says "Moe's" ♪
♪ So enough of your guff ♪
♪ Here's my new idea
to sell both beer and grub ♪
♪ We will turn this
filthy dive ♪
♪ Into a proper old-time
British pub ♪
A British whaaa?
(fanfare plays)
(to tune of "Rule Britannia"):
♪ Darts and meat pies ♪
♪ And lager in pint glasses ♪
♪ What a classy way ♪
♪ To get drunk off
your asses ♪
Hey, hold the phone.
An English pub--
that just might work.
ALL: ♪ In song... ♪
♪ My bar could be British ♪
♪ Instead of arm-pittish,
so why don't we all... ♪
Eh, screw it.
Let's get renovatin'.
(crashing)
Well, I was thinking more like
drapes and a paint job,
but your idea's good, too.
Thanks.
("God Save the Queen" playing)
(indistinct voices)
Pint of ale, my dear?
Well thank you,
Your Honor.
You know,
you're kind of sexy.
That's a deliberate
misstatement of fact.
But I'll allow it.
(gavel bangs, chuckling)
(sighing and moaning)
My first credit card.
Wow, the numbers
are all bumpy-like.
Ha!
So, Mr. Boswell,
what do you think
of the new Moe's?
Marge Simpson
and Moe Szyslak,
here's a mash note
to your bangers--
I wish you could
live in me forever.
Thanks, uh, Freakazoid.
I'd just like to say
that there's one person
to whom I really owe
my newfound success--
Marge Simpson.
Thanks, Moe.
Dad, Mom's spending more time
at Moe's than you are.
And they seem
awfully chummy.
Just what are you inferring?
I'm not inferring
anything.
You infer. I imply.
Whew, that's a relief.
Boy, what a night!
Moe showed me how to give
someone the bum's rush.
Here, watch.
Get lost, rummy!
(grunts)
(chuckling)
Ah, yes, Detroit-style.
Very nice.
So, you've been at Moe's
every night this week.
I know, I used to think of Moe
as a scabby,
dead-eyed hunchback,
but now that I've gotten
to know him, we kind of bonded.
Bonded?!
How many times?
Homer, Moe and I are
just work friends.
You and I are...
marriage friends.
Thanks, honey.
My mind is completely at ease.
(phone ringing)
MOE: Hey, it's me.
Moe!
What's up, partner?
Marge, sorry to call you
so late,
but I had a great idea--
put cutesy signs
outside the restrooms
that say "dukes" and "dames"
instead of the ones
we have now that say
"standups" and "sitdowns."
Huh? Tell me honestly--
what do you think?
Ooh, that's a great idea.
Thanks. Wait, are you sure
I'm not interruptin' anything?
Of course not.
I'm in bed with Homer.
Also, I want to go
with the green...
Well, I might as well use
this pucker for something.
(playing "Greensleeves")
(inhales)
(continues melody)
MALE ANNOUNCER: Coming
this summer from Dreamworks...
52 jokers playing
the game of their lives.
I don't wanna be a three!
-I wanna be a seven!
-(like Jackie Mason):
Shut up, kid.
You're as crazy as an eight,
I'm telling you.
With Eddie Murphy
as the Jack of Clubs.
You don't understand, Officer.
I thought that king
was a queen.
(chuckling)
ANNOUNCER (chuckles):
This summer,
the house is full,
and the deuces are wild!
In Cards!
Hey, Jack,
you got any twos?
(like Jack Nicholson):
You can't handle the twos!
Oh, Marge,
don't you love it
when our hands meet
in the popcorn tub?
Mm-hmm!
(both laughing)
Hey, Marge!
Howdy, partner!
Why don't you sit
next to us?
Hey, Moe.
Haven't seen
you in a while.
Uh, yeah, how ya doing there,
Homer?
Did you ever pass
that G.I. Joe you swallowed?
How do you know about that?
Oh, Marge told me.
We share everything.
You do?
Don't worry.
They're just friends.
There's nothing physical
between them.
Homer, can you hold
my wedding ring for a second?
My finger's itchy.
Uh-oh. I'm gonna have
to work on my marriage.
Or alternatively...
(bird squawks)
(groaning): Oh...
Something wrong, Homer?
Well, I'm worried about
Marge and Moe.
They've developed
an intimate bond
of thoughts and feelings
completely separate from me.
But it's not physical.
So everything's great, right?
Homer, it's time
you learned the sad truth.
Can I learn it
at a happy place?
Moe and Marge are having
an "emotional affair."
Although there's
no physical intimacy,
there's a deep
spiritual connection
that threatens
to destroy your marriage.
What do I do?!
Engage her feelings,
become a friend.
Ooh, get her a Life magazine
from the week she was born.
I'll always treasure mine.
You're absolutely right!
Stop this ride!
(voice cracks):
You're the boss!
(gasping, screaming)
(grunting)
I want to go again,
Daddy!
Daddy?
HOMER: Marge,
my darling!
Thank God you're home!
I've been dying
to hear your feelings!
Oh, I'm too tired
to talk.
Well, I can go all night,
baby.
I could listen to you two,
maybe three times.
Homie, I'm tired.
I have to get up early
to catch my flight.
Catch your flight?
Moe and I are going
to the Tavern
and Restaurant Owners
Convention in Aruba
this weekend.
Don't you ever
listen to me?
I told you ten times.
(snoring)
(clock chimes)
Cuckold! Cuckold! Cuckold!
What's a cuckold?
(spy film music plays)
Where's Mom going
with Uncle Moe?
He's only
your emotional uncle!
I'm your real uncle!
Well, if Hollywood movies
have taught us anything,
it's that troubled relationships
can be completely patched up
by a mad dash to the airport.
I'm off!
PILOT (over speaker):
Folks, welcome
to No Frills Airlines'
flight to Aruba.
Safety instructions
are two dollars.
If you require
wheelchair assistance,
you picked the wrong airline.
Ha, ha.
(gulps)
Uh, you know, Marge,
I've really enjoyed
you working at the bar.
Me, too, Moe.
What a nice surprise
that we've become friends.
MOE: Yeah.
Oh, Marge,
I'm so in love with you.
And tonight,
after some surf 'n' turf
and a bottle of champagne,
maybe some Snickers pie,
I'll explain how the hotel
made a little "mistake"
and we got to stay
in the same room.
(chuckles): Oh, yeah.
Moe, your upper lip
is trembling.
Oh, I'm just excited
because they're showing
an episode of Boy Meets World
on this flight.
Oh no, wait. That's only
on flights from Europe.
We just get
that little plane.
-(beeping)
-Hey, wait a minute.
What the hell is that?
Hang on, Marge!
Homie's coming!
I won't let that man
make you happy!
-(siren wailing)
-(groans): Oh!
Simpson, you were going
a hundred in a 25 zone,
and you're not gonna flirt
your way outta this one.
But I have to get to the airport
to save my marriage!
Really?
Well, why didn't you say so?
Let's roll!
You didn't work this hard
to save my marriage.
Again with that.
Wake up, Lou.
She was way out
of your league.
(siren wailing)
WOMAN (over speaker):
Flight attendants,
prepare for takeoff.
MOE: Time for some shuba-duba
in Aruba.
Oh, my God!
Moe, did you see something
troubling on the tarmac?
No. Why do you say that?
You got to get
me closer, Chief!
Anything for love!
(grunts)
(tires screeching)
Okay, time to chase this pig
into the sty.
Uh, Marge, you deserve a man
who listens to you,
who respects you,
who understands
what a treasure
you really are.
I don't know what to say.
Just say you love me,
Marge.
Love me like I love you.
Please?
HOMER: Marge...!
-That sounds like Homer.
-No it isn't.
I don't hear nothin'.
You're crazy.
Get outta here.
Will you marry me?
MARGE: Homer?!
How'd you get in here?
Toilet hole.
Brrr!
-You leave my wife alone!
-You don't deserve her!
You know
nothing about Marge.
What's her favorite food?
Uh... ice?
Wrong! It's buttered noodles.
He's right.
Oh, it's true.
I don't know Marge at all.
I'll just go home now.
Aah! Waah! Aah!
Aah!
(screaming)
Shut it! Shut it!
(groans)
Moe, you've won.
I'll see you
at baggage claim.
Hot damn, I won!
Marge, I swear I'll be
the best man you ever had.
It's gonna be all flowers
and back rubs
and "How was your day,
dear?" and...
Moe!
No, I don't love you.
And I'm certainly not going
to leave my husband.
You mean I listened to all
your touchy-feely yip-yap
for nothing?
I'm afraid so.
At least I had a couple
of sips from your Coke
when you went
to the bathroom.
(sobbing)
Homie...
Marge,
I just want to say,
if you ever feel like
cheating on Moe,
here's my card.
Homer, I made a vow
on our wedding day
to stay by you,
for better or worse.
And besides, I love you.
You're my Homie-womie-
romie-domie.
And you're my
Margie-wargie-bargie-fargie-
gargie-margie-
targie-largie.
I may have dodged
a bullet here.
(calypso music playing)
Might as well face it,
I'll never find anyone.
Come on tide,
take me with ya.
I just don't want to feel
no more pain.
(muffled):
Ow. Ow! Ow!
Moe, I need
to tell you something.
(ripping)
(gasps): Ow!
You showed me you could be
a really sweet guy.
You can make a woman
very happy someday.
Wow. For realsies?
It's true.
You'd be quite a catch...
if you'd just
shower and shave
and stop swearing
under your breath.
Aw, thanks, Marge.
(under breath):
Know-it-all bitch.
Oh, uh, did I mention there was
a mistake at the front desk?
(sneaky chuckling)
Really?
Is it one that will change
the sleeping arrangements?
Could be. Could be.
(chuckles)
Listen, I got to tell you,
I chew in my sleep.
Yeah, well,
I sweat blood.
Good night, both of you.
(gasps):
Who's watching the kids?
Are you sure Mom and Dad
want us to enter
a European balloon race?
Sure. Why not?
("La Vie en Rose" playing)
MARGE: ♪ Love ♪
♪ Love will keep us together ♪
♪ Think of me, babe,
whenever ♪
♪ Some sweet-talking guy
in a thong ♪
♪ Hands you a bong ♪
♪ Don't take a hit ♪
♪ You just
got to be strong ♪
MARGE:
♪ You better stop ♪
HOMER: ♪ 'Cause I want
a sandwich ♪
♪ I said stop ♪
♪ Or maybe a Manwich ♪
Shh!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem