CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
-Huh?
-(groaning)
Check it out, girls:
68 squares of
ankle-busting fury.
That's right, a double-dogleg,
hamstring-knotting
Hop-Way to Hell.
What insane kangaroo dreamed
this fevered nightmare?
Behold.
Ladies, grab your pebbles.
Mmm!
(giggles)
-What?
-Nothing.
(laughter)
(with singsong voice):
Lisa has a big butt.
ALL:
Shut up! I do not!
Oh no. Don't make
Lisa mad.
She might crush us all
with her giant butt.
Shut up, you.
Stop teasing
the big-bottomed lass.
She's just as God made her--
plump as a Christmas goose.
LISA: Dad...
the kids at school
said my butt's big.
That's ridiculous, honey.
You're the cutest
little girl I know.
You just have
what is known
as the Simpson butt.
Permit me to elaborate.
Every Simpson starts
with a circle.
Daddy has one big circle
here...
...then a smaller one up
two big, sexy circles
for eyes...
one macho muzzle...
then a snappy new outfit.
Ooh, I'm looking good.
Ooh, cuffs. Yeah.
And for some reason,
my hair and ear
form an "M" and a "G".
Party! Party!
Hmm?
You want to know
a little trick?
To downsize my derriere,
I just tie a sweater around it.
See?
(whimpering)
(falsetto voice):
Oh, Homer,
you're wasting
away to nothing.
You simply must eat something.
(normal voice):
Well, you're the boss.
(falsetto voice):
Oh, I love to see my man eat.
Check it out, Homes.
You said if I ever got
a hundred on a test,
You'd throw me a party.
There's my hundred--
Where's my party?
(scoffs)
Nice try, loser.
I bet you made up
a fake test.
Nope, it's real--
check out the watermark.
All right.
D'oh!
Aha. Here's a mistake.
It says the capital
of Kentucky is Frankfort.
(chuckles)
Dream on, pal.
Homer, the capital of Kentucky
is Frankfort.
Really?
Frankfurter...
is that anything?
(sighs)
Yes, it's something, dear.
See, it's all legit.
Now make with the party.
All right, boy, which con
did you work here?
Copy off another kid?
Pay attention and take notes?
Well, take note of this.
(grunting)
(laughing)
(gagging)
Bart really did
get a hundred.
I gave a test on state
capitals, but I forgot to roll
up the map.
Everyone got a hundred.
I win. P-A-R-T. Par-tee.
(party horn squealing)
People, please.
It's a school night.
I thought
you two broke up.
This means nothing.
Yes, yes, you've
made that quite clear.
Maybe a different outfit would
make me look thinner.
Hmm.
(groans)
This store makes me feel
even worse about myself.
(electronic beat)
Oh.
I heard she's back
to her birth weight.
Must be nice.
Ew.
No, no, the body on this
mannequin is all wrong.
I know.
It's such an unrealistic
standard for young... huh?
(singing to the tune of
"Bringing in the Sheaves"):
♪ Planing down the thighs,
planing down the thighs ♪
♪ I make four bucks an hour
Hey, I don't look so bad.
Don't worry, Lisa.
You can still find
someone to love you.
Now you've got no choice.
No!
Oh boy, Barty's gonna party.
He sure is--
if he can keep up with
these party animals:
Aunt Patty, Aunt Selma,
Grandma Bouvier and...
(imitating fanfare)
Grampa.
(snoring)
Plus your school-yard chums:
Martin and Ralph.
Bart's my bestest
boyfriend.
Oh Mom, this
guest list sucks.
It's the best I could do
on such short notice.
Aw, where's Milhouse?
He's got the measles.
But we've got him on
speakerphone.
(static-filled voice):
Rock on.
You know, the first time
I met Bart
was at recess in first
grade...
(signal breaks up)
Oh, I told him
to use a land line.
Okay, gang, let's get
this party started--
or should I say Barted? Huh?
For our first game,
I need everyone to draw a
picture of President
Eisenhower.
I drew him with
Canadian Prime Minister
Louis St. Laurent.
Their relationship was
frosty at best.
(moans)
Duck, duck, duck, duck, duck,
duck, duck, duck, duck, duck,
duck, duck, duck, duck,
duck, duck, duck,
duck, duck, duck, duck...
Say "goose," you stupid freak.
(crying)
(whimpers)
Oh, Mom, this was
the worst party ever.
(groaning)
Gee, I did
the best I could...
Here's Lisa.
She'll save the party.
Honey, sit down.
Have a big slice of cake.
What? I'm not
fat enough already?
How could you say that to me?
(crying)
Lisa, wait...
(huffing)
MILHOUSE:
Hello? Hello?
I had to leave 'cause my
French bread pizza dinged.
Hello?
Duck, duck, duck, duck, duck,
duck, duck, duck, duck, duck,
duck, duck, duck, duck,
duck, duck, duck, duck...
HOMER:
Oh, what's the big deal?
Bart didn't like
his presents. So what?
It's not like he gives us
such great gifts.
Remember that maple leaf
ironed between
the sheets of wax paper?
What was that?
That was crap.
Oh, it's not
just the presents.
The kids don't
appreciate me anymore.
They'd rather hang out
with their friends
than with their mom.
So they're growing up.
Soon they'll be
leaving the nest,
and you'll have time
for yourself--
hundreds
of thousands of hours,
and then,
the peace of the grave.
No! No, I've got
a lot more mothering
left in me.
I'll be right here at
3:00 to pick you up.
Then I'll take
you to the zoo.
We can eat fries
out of a safari hat!
No, thanks. I'm going
to stay in the library
and do a little reading.
Oh!
Well, I guess it's
just you and me, Bart!
Mom, after that
lame party you threw,
I'd rather hang out
with thunder-thighs here.
(groans)
They grow up so fast.
They're just asserting
their independence.
If a child doesn't do it now,
it may never happen.
Seymour! Do you want your
vitamin in applesauce?
Or are you gonna take it
like a big boy?
Applesauce.
(Maggie giggles)
Oh, sure, you love
me now, but you'll turn.
(grunting)
Stop struggling,
and get in my mouth, jerks!
Aren't you the boy
who beats up my son?
Prob'ly.
What's your name?
Simpson.
Oh, yeah. Bart Simpson.
Spiky hair, soft kidneys,
always hitting himself?
Those tadpoles
are your lunch?
Technically, brunch.
Well, here, take this.
My daughter didn't want
the lunch I made.
(sniffing)
Mmm. This sandwich rocks.
My tadpoles seem crude
by comparison.
Ha-ha! You're
nocturnal.
You don't have to impress me
by making fun of others.
I already like you.
Ha-ha.
I'm starting to let
down my guard. Ha-ha!
Thanks, Mrs. S.
Today didn't
totally suck nard.
It's nice to be
appreciated.
Whatever.
Take it sleazy.
Mom?!
Nelson? I thought you
were sleeping
in the park tonight.
Oh, that's okay,
the kid don't
bother me none.
Hey, Nelson,
say hello to Moe.
He said he'd
take you camping sometime.
I said I might.
MARGE:
Hey, kids,
I just heard they canceled
league night down
at the bowling alley.
You know what that means?
Open lanes!
Whaddya say?
It'll be BLAM!
Bart, Lisa And Mom. Huh?
Mom, when I want
lame and needy,
I'll call Milhouse.
No offense.
Fine!
I'll take
my mothering elsewhere.
Yeah!
Ooh, great
roll, Nelson.
Here, I cut up your
hot dog for you.
Wow, hot dogs are awesome!
You've never had one before?
No, but I saw some
in a catalog once.
People in sweaters
were eating them at a picnic.
So, my mom works at Hooters,
but her dream is to go
to Vegas and work
in a real strip club.
(growls)
And, uh, where's
your dad in all this?
He went out for a pack
of cigarettes
and never came back.
He said "smell ya later,"
but he never smelled me again.
(sobbing)
Nelson, how'd you like
to earn some extra money
around our house?
I have some odd jobs
my kids won't do.
Yeah.
I get the feeling
Bart isn't
everything he could be
in the son department.
Sometimes I think
he's more interested
in his "Itchy and Mitchy"
cartoons than me.
Hey, I'm sure
it's just a phase,
like when I used
to stand on the overpass
and drop computers
on the freeway.
Uh-huh. That's how
we got our Kaypro.
64, 65, 66...
Hey, Lisa.
Are you counting
how many days
it takes to wash
your big butt?
(giggling)
I can't hear you.
That's because your
butt blocks your ears.
That doesn't make any sense.
Neither does
your butt.
(giggling)
(growls)
LISA:
I know this obsession
with thinness
is unhealthy and
anti-feminist...
but that's what a
fat girl would say.
Lis, look!
(gasps)
Now, I know there's
a handsome young man
behind all that
hair and dirt.
Hmm. Maybe not,
but you did a great
job on the lawn.
Thanks, Dingus...
I mean, ma'am.
My mother...
my bully...
my God!
MARGE:
Lisa,
just take a bite.
One bite-- that's all I ask!
(groans)
Now, I can't have
toothpaste tonight.
Oh...
(doorbell ringing)
Here's the money
you gave my son.
We don't want
your charity.
I didn't give
your son charity.
I gave him self-respect.
Self-respect, huh?
No wonder he came home with
his vest all buttoned--
like he was somebody.
Go home to your son,
Mrs. Muntz,
and try not to have
intercourse on the way!
(cat hisses, screeches)
Nelson, what are you
doing out this late?
My mom ditched me!
She went to Hollywood
to be an actress,
but her range is limited!
(sobbing)
Oh, she's still your mother.
Come inside.
Huh?
Can I get you
a glass of milk?
Cow milk?!
Uh-huh.
(surprised yell)
What are you doing
in my jammies?
I'm your new roommate.
I call top bunk.
But...
it's a single bed.
I said top bunk!
(sighs)
(humming)
Mom, the reason God
invented dead bolts
is to keep people like
Nelson out of your house.
Bart, have you ever eaten
a Tootsie Pop?
You know, there's
a tough, crunchy shell,
but if you lick it,
there's a delicious
sweetness inside.
Be nice to Nelson,
and I'll give you a Tootsie Pop.
Morning, losers.
Mrs. Simpson.
Pancakes,
my favorite!
Mm... mm...
Bart, eat up or you'll
be late for school.
I'm not hungry.
-Ugh!
-You heard the lady,
clean your plate!
(gulping)
Savor it.
Let the flavors dance
on your palate.
Mm...
Mm... mm...
(nervous chuckle):
Mm...
TV ANNOUNCER:
Next on ABC,
who's dropping by
to see George Lopez?
We pray it's you!
Open.
Nelson, doesn't that
hurt your teeth?
(grunts):
My teeth hurt all the time.
I just try to think
about motorcycles.
I don't like
the sound of that.
Tomorrow I'm taking you
to Dr. Shapiro.
A doctor
for your teeth?
What's next, a lawyer
for your hair?
(stifled chuckle)
(owl hooting)
(creaking)
NELSON:
♪ Papa, can you hear me? ♪
♪ Papa, can you see me? ♪
♪ Papa, can you find me
in the night? ♪
♪ Papa, are you near me? ♪
♪ Papa, can you hear me? ♪
♪ Papa, can you help me
not be frightened? ♪
♪ Looking at the skies
I seem to see a million eyes ♪
♪ Which ones are yours? ♪
(cries)
I gotta do something
about him.
-(refrigerator door opens)
-Huh?
This is the perfect test.
If I can have one dab
of frosting and then stop,
I'll know I've conquered
food at last.
That was too easy.
(crazed giggling)
Okay, if I stop here,
I still have some dignity.
(crazed cackling)
Well, at least she's
not singing Streisand.
(cackling)
Hey Lis, still insecure
about your body?
(clears throat)
Yeah, a little.
Those mean girls
just get to me.
I understand.
I have a sister--
I think she's dead now--
who had the same problem.
And I know just the solution.
Sherri. Terri.
The only thing sweeter
than you two
are these stolen cookies.
Enjoy.
(giggling)
Thank you, Nelson.
(screaming)
(laughs)
(sung to "Jingle Bells"):
♪ Sherri smells, Terri smells ♪
♪ Stinky all the way ♪
♪ Stink-stink stink,
stink-stink stink ♪
♪ One-horse open sleigh ♪
(yelling)
Thank you, Nelson.
He who haw haws last,
haw haws best.
I really appreciate
you teaching
those mean girls a lesson.
Tomorrow I can
bleach a swear word
into their hair.
I'd like that.
Nelson?
Papa!
You came back!
(sobbing)
I never meant
to leave you, Nelson.
But something awful happened
when I went to the store.
Well, that
explains a lot.
-Who's hungry?
-No.
I want to hear what happened
at the store.
Well, I went in
to buy cigarettes...
Could you gift-wrap
them, please?
They're for my son.
I also bought myself
a candy bar,
which, uh, unfortunately
was filled with peanuts,
to which I am allergic.
(mumbling gibberish)
-(bellowing)
-I ran outside
just as the circus was
rolling into town.
(percussion plays)
(babbling)
(laughter)
BART:
And that's where I found him.
I brought him back here
so he could take Nelson away,
and my bruises would heal.
I want to give you
a home again, son.
MRS. MUNTZ:
And so do I.
Mom!
I got an acting job.
From the third director
I slept with.
I play Lady MacBeth.
I don't have
to take my top off,
but I do anyway.
Well, I'm glad everything
worked out so well.
Yep. The Muntzes are
back in business.
Yep, the Four
Muntzes.
Eh...
Thanks for finding
my Dad, Bart.
And thanks, lady,
for making me feel
good about myself.
So, now that
you're happy again,
I guess you won't beat me up
at school anymore.
I wish it were
that simple.
I really do.
They're a family again.
And so are we.
What happened?
(groans)
Sometimes you have
to adopt your son's bully
in order to bring your
own family temporarily closer.
And Lisa, what
have you learned?
Nothing.
Like many women,
I still have an unhealthy
obsession with my weight.
But talking
about the problem
is the first
step towards
the solution, right?
I guess.
But there's
a long way to go.
(mutters)
Come on, say something
conclusive.
I'm afraid this is
a very open-ended problem.
HOMER (groans):
Oh, open-ended?!
(crying):
Oh, come on, Lisa.
Say everything's fine.
HOMER (high-pitched voice):
Everything's fine.
LISA: That was you.
HOMER: Prove it.
(Homer chuckles)
Shh!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem