CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(all grunting)
MALE ANNOUNCER:
And with time running out,
the Seminoles
are on the warpath.
Go, Seminoles!
(chanting):
Cover the point spread.
(sniffs, grunts)
ANNOUNCER: Here's the play
that will determine the game.
(gasps)
ANNOUNCER 2:
Stay tuned for Sitcom Sunday.
(muttering)
Where's the remote?
This is not a drill, people.
(whimpering)
(grunts)
-(groans)
(barks)
Hmm,
the TV changes channels
every time
the dog barks.
(barks)
We return to Mel Gibson's
The Salad of the Christ
on Christian Carrot Theater.
I think he swallowed
the remote.
Barf for your master.
(whimpering)
(barking)
Lousy American-made dog.
Oh!
Oh, why must I be
so voluptuous?
Oh.
Ooh,
time to make you pretty.
(groans)
Oh yes,
add more color.
(whimpers):
How do I look?
-(groans)
-Ow!
Oh, after my makeover I'm gonna
get you boy.
MAN: Yo, yo, yo.
Here now the nizzews.
The top artists in hip-hop
are coming to Springfield.
This all-star concert,
dubbed "Murder 4 Life,"
features Da Glock Pointaz,
Romeo Smoov,
Queen Booty Shaykah,
M.C. Champagne Millionaire,
and Assault Weapons magazine's
Man of the Year, Alcatraaaz.
Alcatraaaz is wide spread.
I'm talkin' da junk.
Just what we need--
another lame suburban kid
who loves rap.
So? You like the blues.
Yes, but the blues
are unpopular.
Man, are you illin'.
Rappers stopped saying
"illin'" 12 years ago.
I'm keepin' it real.
They stopped saying "keepin'
it real" three years ago.
Mom, Lisa's dissin' me.
"Dissin'"?
Do rappers still say that?
(frustrated groan)
Dad, can I go to a rap
concert?
Tickets are $50.
Go to hell.
Okay, what if I pay
for it myself?
Fine, go nuts.
I love you, Dad.
I love you too, Jerry.
Baggy britches?
Loose-laced gym shoes?
Are you going
to a rap performance?
Hell, yeah.
I'm representin'
at "Murder 4 Life,"
know what I'm sayin'?
All too well.
Rap music belongs
in the rubbish bin.
It encourages punching,
boastfulness,
and rudeness to hos.
Step off, Mom.
Rap is the poetry
of the streets.
Well, you are not going
to any concert
that promulgates
stink talk.
(whining):
But Dad already
said I could go.
Oh, did he?
Homer, you tell your son
a rap show is not a safe
place for a ten-year-old.
Son, your mother
makes a very loud point.
But you said I could go
if I paid for the ticket.
Boy, let me explain
the situation
in terms
you'll understand.
(beatboxing)
(rapping):
♪ You did it on the straight ♪
♪ Got your dad's permission ♪
♪ But your mom
dropped a bomb ♪
♪ So I flipped
my position ♪
♪ Don't argue with Marge,
I know what's best ♪
♪ The only rap in this crib
keeps sandwiches fresh ♪
♪ Fresh, fr-fresh
for Mommy's baby boy ♪
♪ Baby boy, baby boy ♪
♪ Ba-ba-ba-baby boy. ♪
(yells)
Dad,
you completely sold me out.
Well, I paid for this ticket.
That makes me an adult.
I'm going.
I love you, Krusty-wusty.
(crowd cheering)
(hip-hop music playing)
♪ Every miner '49er
and stone-cold conniver ♪
♪ Stakes a claim on my tongue
to pan my saliva ♪
♪ Make the hos drop
they clothes like
they Lady Godiva. ♪
Whoa!
♪ Yo, cuz, put down my mic
'less you know how to use it ♪
♪ This is old school
not preschool ♪
♪ So don't Dr. Seuss it. ♪
(audience laughing)
(gulps)
♪ Don't critique
my technique ♪
♪ I'm no geek,
I make the principal nervous ♪
-(music playing)
-♪ My friends
can confirm this ♪
♪ I'll bust a spitwad
in your epidermis ♪
Oh, no he didn't.
♪ You can trace my remorse
to its supersized source ♪
♪ A hungry, hungry hypocrite
named Homer, of course ♪
♪ My old man's pathetic ♪
♪ Damn, is his head thick ♪
♪ The gas from his ass
is carcinogenic ♪
♪ Every day I pray
his DNA ain't genetic. ♪
(audience cheering)
(hip-hop music plays)
Damn, this ride is
pimped-out.
Yo, downstairs
I got a wax museum
of famous movie monsters.
Check it out
if you want
to get your fright on.
Jeepers, it's 50 Cent.
Yo, B, I heard
you throw down on stage.
Wanna join my world tour?
Sorry, Fiddy.
I have school tomorrow.
You're right--
the more, you know,
the further you'll go.
And that's one to grow on.
-Does that count
as community service?
-No.
A'ight,
take me to the park.
We'll pick up
some dog poo.
Yes, sir.
Here you go,
you little yellow cracker.
Now let's go
murder our enemies.
Peace.
Bart's gone.
I checked everywhere.
That little sneak disobeyed us
and went
to that hip-hop festival.
If that's true,
he's gonna be like NWA--
Not Without Ass-welts.
(gulps):
Well, time to face
my punishment like a man.
Or... lie my way out of it
like a kid.
A flying rock.
Call a geologist.
(groans)
Hmm.
"We have kidnapped your son.
Follow instructions,
and Bart will not be harmed."
"Follow instructions"?!
He's doomed!
(sobbing)
This'll be the worst
Thanksgiving dinner ever.
Thanksgiving's
not for months.
The bad news keeps on coming.
(sobbing)
Tragedy climbed
a ladder last night
as ten-year-old Bart Simpson
was snatched from his bed,
his chocolate milk dreams
cut short by kidnapping fiends.
Mrs. Simpson,
is the pain so unbearable
you wish your son
had never been born?
What a horrible thing
to say to a mother.
(crying)
Perhaps reading this message
aloud will comfort you.
It's "Win a Hawaiian Getaway
Week" on Channel Six.
(crying)
So, mail in those
pineapple stickers today.
Aloha means
"one entry per person."
(crying)
I will find Bart Simpson.
Clancy Wiggum is on the case.
(laughter)
Chief, seriously.
Shouldn't we just plan
for the funeral?
Hey,
I crack cases all the time.
Like the case
of the symphony conductor
who murdered
his star cellist.
That was an episode
of Columbo, Chief.
They show you
who the bad guy is
at the beginning
of each one.
Yeah, but you have to remember.
This is no fun without Bart.
(sighs)
He used to watch me
while I did this.
BART: I still do.
Bart.
Are the kidnappers
after you?
Well, some kidnappers
might be after me.
It's a big world.
But in this case,
I faked the whole thing.
Why, are you mad at me?
No, it's not about you.
Ah, it's never about me.
(grunts)
Look, I need
a place to hide out
till the heat is off.
In my dad's apartment,
the heat is always off.
He made a coat out
of all my stuffed animals.
(shivers)
You can hide out
in my room.
My dad won't know
'cause he's at work.
Shoo. Get out of here.
These aren't your soybeans.
Wow, I should have read these
headlines a long time ago.
Together,
they really paint a picture...
of failure.
And now my only friend
is the bottle.
(munching)
(snoring)
MAN: Rise and shine,
Chief Wiggum.
This pity party is over.
Wha... officer down... huh?
Barney Fife.
Y-E-S spells you got it,
buster.
And I'm here to tell you
the feelings you're having
are common for every (sniffs)
brother of the badge.
Well, my fat grew over
my badge.
Aw, sour mash.
It's time for you
to roll up your sleeves
and get the old (sniffs)
crime sniffer out
on the street.
You're right.
I've gotta buckle down
and do some police work.
Now that's the can-do attitude
that puts dudes in the can.
(chuckles)
Well, I'm wanted
back on the set.
Set? Are you the character
or the actor who plays him?
(spookily):
Now I must go...
Wait a minute,
now you're a ghost?
Avenge me.
(phone ringing)
Hello?
BART (angrily):
This is the kidnapper.
Do what I say
and Bart won't get hurt.
Oh, yeah?
Send a finger wrapped
in today's paper
to prove you have him.
Homer!
I know what I'm doing.
You can use
any section of the paper.
Except Metro.
It's a big snooze.
Please give me back my boy.
I just want to tell him
I love him one more time.
(sobbing)
Mom, it's me.
Don't cry, I'm okay.
The kidnappers say
if you worry too much...
they'll kill me.
(sobbing)
-Uh, no, no, I mean...
-(popping)
Okay,
you made your point.
Gotta go.
All right, boys.
Let's get this tape back
to the lab for analysis.
We have a lab?
Yeah, it's that room we keep
the Christmas decorations in.
BART: No, no, I mean...
What is that noise
in the background?
Maybe I can isolate it.
(popping)
I know I've heard
that noise before.
Think, Clancy, think.
Hail falling on a tin roof?
No.
That's it!
Stovetop popcorn.
And it sounds like my favorite
brand-- Chintzy-Pop!
Eddie, Lou,
we're going
to the Kwik-E-Mart.
You already sent us
there twice today.
Nah, that was for snacks.
This time...
it's not personal.
WIGGUM:
I need the name of everyone
who buys Chintzy-Pop popcorn.
Oh, Chintzy-Pop
is the worst legal popcorn.
Many of the kernels
are baby teeth.
There are only
two idiots
cheap enough to buy
this crap.
You and...
Oh, baby,
is there anything better
than video poker
and Chintzy-Pop?
Whoa!
I'm looking
at an inside straight.
(buzzer sounds)
Oh, some day I'll hear
the winning music.
Some day.
Drop the corn,
tightey-whitey!
What?
I didn't do anything.
We'll let a judge be
the judge of that.
Yo, Chief,
we found the kid!
Wow. For once
I did everything right.
What's going on?
I didn't know he was here.
I swear!
Uh, Chief...
Is Milhouse's Dad
gonna be in trouble?
He's not really a bad guy.
Now, now,
there's no need for you
to defend your captor,
Bratty Hearst.
We're putting you
in a dirty little cell.
Not as small and dirty
as this apartment,
but you know,
it's still pretty bad.
Oh, Bart, I'm so glad
you're okay.
Oh, son.
Taking your tombstone
back to the store
will be the happiest thing
I've ever done.
¡Ay caramba!
Chief, we're sorry
we didn't have faith in you.
And I'm sorry
I wrote those
letters-to-the-editor
calling for your ouster.
You're "Worried
In West Springfield?"
Not any more, Chief.
Not any more.
Keep those rose petals coming.
I almost stepped
on regular ground back there.
(crowd cheering)
Bart, two, three, four!
You put my Dad in jail,
flip, spin, twirl!
Milhouse, if you tell anyone,
I'll tell the world
you wet your pants
watching Harry Potter.
I wasn't scared,
I was just peeing.
Look, if you tell
what I did,
I'll get in trouble.
You gotta do
something.
I want my Dad back!
(grunts)
(playing
"Stars and Stripes")
You've got the perfect build
for a suit-- 44 regular.
(whispering):
56 huge.
Boys, even though I've been
made Police Commissioner,
don't think
I've forgotten you.
Lou, you're promoted
to Chief of Police.
Sweet.
And Eddie,
you're promoted to Lou.
Nice.
And, uh,
who's gonna be Eddie?
We don't need an Eddie.
Commissioner Wiggum,
I need
to confess something.
Is it that you're proud
of me?
I lied about
being kidnapped.
The whole thing
was a hoax.
A hoax? A hoax?!
(groans)
Bart, please,
you can't take this
away from me.
How would I explain it
to Ralphie?
That kid can't understand
where the world goes
when you close the drapes.
But...
what about Milhouse's Dad?
Hey, this is the best thing
that ever happened
to that loser.
Women love famous felons.
(women screaming)
Kirk, you are so dangerous--
and misunderstood!
You've kidnapped my heart!
I love the way
I've heard of you!
So Bart, as you can see,
from what I just said,
everyone is a winner here.
(birds squawking)
Huh?
(gasps)
A shirt from that rap concert.
Bart must've gone to the show.
But that means...
Bart was never
kidnapped?
Lisa, I'm very glad
you brought me this.
I'll see that it gets
to the proper authorities.
Dad!?
Why did you do that?
Hollywood producers
have paid me a fortune,
which I've already lost,
for the rights
to Bart's story.
So I have to destroy anything
that proves
that story's not true.
Why did you burn up
your shirt?
What shirt?
I don't see any shirt.
Burn the truth.
(sighs)
So you see,
Principal Skinner,
that's why I had
to come to you.
Wait, why did your father
burn his pants?
It doesn't matter.
The point is...
only with your help
can I expose Bart's lies.
A chance to bring down
Bart Simpson?
Our school's second most-wanted
criminal after the mysterious
El Barto?
Sign me up!
Boys, let me tell ya.
Now that I'm commissioner,
the shaves are hotter,
the steaks are thicker
and I've got
my own private bathroom,
so Lou here
won't be using
my sonic toothbrush
on his rotten choppers--
Yuck!
Uh, listen,
Commissioner.
Lisa Simpson
came by the office today,
asking questions about her
brother's kidnapping.
Questions?
Yes, as if she were
trying
to unravel
a tapestry of deceit.
All right, people,
we got a situation here.
Your daughter's gonna blow
our whole deal sky high.
You leave Maggie to me.
No, Lisa.
Not her!
She'll hunt us down
relentlessly--
like a bloodhound mixed
with a student loan officer.
Hey, I can't leave this place!
I get three square
meals a day
and trailer time with
Springfield's craziest chicks.
(screaming)
Hey, I got
the most to lose here.
I just printed up
10,000 business cards.
How am I going to pass
all these out
before she catches me?
Give me
a call sometime!
Give me a call sometime!
Ah! Here comes the panic!
People, please.
The only way
Lisa can bust me.
Is if she finds
someone who can prove
I was at that rap show.
And I know just where she can
find that someone.
Let's go cover our asses!
Wait, before we go,
I took the liberty of making
these embroidered conspiracy
jackets for all of us.
Wow, those jackets
are beautiful.
We must never wear them.
Mr. Alcatraaaz,
my name is Lisa Simpson
and this is
Principal Skinner.
Hi.
Would you mind showing us
video footage
of your last concert?
No problem.
I've got
a 200-inch plasma TV.
In my shoe closet.
(laughing)
(chuckles)
I'm sharing a laugh
with my new friends.
♪ Homer is a fat load ♪
CROWD:
This proves Bart lied
about being kidnapped.
Not yet.
Can we verify exactly
what time Bart was at the show?
If only we had
the exact date.
Bingo!
Thank you,
Mr. Alcatraaaz.
Ain't nothin'.
Ah, ah, ah.
"It is nothing."
It's idiomatic, biatch.
(grunts)
All right, hand over the tape
and nobody gets hurt.
(guns cocking)
Ah, this is hopeless.
My gun isn't even loaded.
Aw, nuts.
They're gonna release that tape
and our hoax will be exposed.
Well, I guess
I'll go back to Baltimore
and sell ribbon
with my Daddy.
Ribbon! Get your ribbon!
Great for presents!
(sighs)
Wait a minute.
Why do we have
to come clean?
Nobody's been hurt.
Everyone's happier
with the lie.
The lie is love.
Wait just a minute.
Love the lie!
The way I was raised,
by Mom,
I learned the truth
can't be swept under the rug.
That's a very noble
sentiment, Lisa.
But for once in your life,
can't you just be cool?
Yeah, be cool.
Like us.
Coolee, coolee cool!
Come on, fool!
Be coolee, coolee cool!
-(guns cocking)
-(shrieks)
Yo, put away
your Glocks, man.
Yes, share with us
the wisdom
of the street,
oh, mighty Alcatraaaz.
There are times in life
when the truth
ain't black nor white,
but a subtler
shade of gray, yo.
And when the path of justice
is obscured
by the fog of uncertainty,
there is only one solution.
House party!
(rap music playing)
I don't understand.
After all the corruption
and deceit we've witnessed,
how can everyone
just party?
Lisa, the world is
a very complicated place.
When you get
right down to it...
Cannonball!
Do you think
there's a place
in the hip-hop world
for a 40-something
elementary school
administrator?
Hell yes.
Mmm.
But I'm already payin'
a guy for that.
Skinner!
I order you to step off,
dog.
(laughing)
I think they're making
fun of me,
but my wife
is very sick.
Shh!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem