CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
MALE ANNOUNCER: We now return
to Blackula Meets Black Dracula
I'm turning this disco
into a hockey rink.
You mean a "honky rink"!
(screaming)
You know, Black Dracula
is now a Congressman
from Virginia.
(humming)
Bart, where did
you get those?
There's an open house next door.
They're giving out
cookies and business cards!
Check it out.
I'm a business jerk!
Marge, I don't want
to buy this house.
I'd have to live
next door to myself.
(loud music playing)
Turn that down!
Screw you!
Uh!
Relax,
we're just looky-loos.
We're only here
to compare our lifestyle
to our neighbors.
Oh, come on, Marge.
It's not fair to compare us
to an American household.
(gasps)
It's so beautiful
and modern.
Ooh, a Sub-Zero fridge.
A slightly colder fridge?
In my lifetime? Amazing.
This is the kitchen
I've always wanted.
Ooh, a bread maker-maker!
(mechanical beep)
And check this out.
A walk-in microwave!
Hey, Marge, can you press "stop"
when my popcorn's done?
Uh-oh.
(Marge humming)
-(silverware clangs)
-(gasps)
(dress rips)
(gasps)
(groaning)
Homie, when I married you,
I knew we wouldn't
live in luxury.
And I kept that vow.
(table leg cracks)
But seeing that kitchen today
made me wish we had something
a little better for ourselves.
I'll build you
a new kitchen, sweetie.
Aww, Homie...
that's so thoughtful,
but maybe we should hire
a professional contractor.
A contractor?
Those guys are
the biggest crooks around.
They charge for materials
and labor!
Pick one, jerks!
(Homer humming)
(painful groan)
Man, that hurt.
And now to do
the exact same thing again.
(painful groans)
Maybe you should
turn off the power.
All right.
Don't demolish along the way!
Fine.
Easy, easy.
Playdude magazines?
Have you been hiding
bosom rags from me?
Trying to.
These magazines are from
before we were married.
Maybe you should
throw them away.
But I need them
for the articles!
The articles, eh?
So you wouldn't mind if
I cut out all the erotic nudes?
Of course not.
Why would I want
to look at a nude woman
I'm not even married to?
I mean, I wouldn't even know
how she could improve me.
"I'm not wearing any clothes.
So why don't I just splay
myself on a pool table"?
(groans)
Steady, steady...
Okay, here's
your precious articles.
Thanks, Marge,
I can't wait to read
about "Sport Fishing
with Sonny Jurgensen."
(sobbing)
What man would want you now?
Whoa! Playdudes!
Let the blossoming
of Milhouse begin.
I gotta be honest,
I don't see what
all the hubbub is about.
Hey, the lady
in this picture is hot.
She can Calamine
my hives anytime.
That's Congresswoman
Bella Abzug.
MILHOUSE:
Ciao Bella.
The grown-ups in
this magazine are pretty cool.
I could make the tree house
look like this.
Then we could have orgies,
whatever they are.
We'll be Playdude
Playmates!
BOTH:
We are Playdude Playmates!
There it is,
nice and smooth.
I'd like to see your boyfriend
the contractor do a better job.
I think you used
too much plaster.
Oh, now you tell me.
I never stopped telling you.
So that's what that
white noise was.
I'm calling a contractor.
Thanks for taking the job.
I'm sorry my husband
is being so difficult.
Get lost, crook!
That's all right,
Mrs. Simpson.
Many husbands
feel emasculated
when their wife must turn
to a professional
to satisfy her
remodeling needs.
(grumbling):
Why don't you just kiss her?
I'm gay.
But I have a subcontractor
that does that sort
of thing for me.
I like-a to kiss.
(kissing)
Now, don't you worry.
Your kitchen will be
done in three weeks.
When Virginia Woolf wrote,
"Every woman needs
a room of one's own,"
she must have been talking
about the kitchen.
What's the first thing you're
gonna make in your new kitchen?
How 'bout cooking up some money
because this stupid kitchen
cost $100,000.
(sobbing)
I was thinking
of chicken wings.
Those are good too.
Same old stuff:
meatloaf, casserole, tuna loaf,
loaferole, casseloaf...
Marge Simpson's
Wasabi Buffalo Wings!
Ooh, an Eastern twist on
a western New York favorite.
These wings are going straight
to my thighs...
and I say bon voyage!
What do you think,
Thomas Pynchon?
These wings
are "V-licious!"
I'll put this recipe
in the Gravity's
Rainbow Cookbook,
right next to
The Frying of Latke 49.
I agree with my fellow
Cornell alumnus!
Huzzah for Marge!
ALL:
Huzzah!
And how 'bout a huzzah
for my husband
who paid for our new kitchen?
Never!
Marge, you know, I thought
I was Springfield's
wing ding king, but, uh,
you make my chicken look
like cock-a-diddily doo-doo.
Great stuff, Ned.
You know I was gonna enter
this here Ovenfresh Bakeoff...
but up against you, I wouldn't
have a Hindu's chance in heaven.
If you win,
Ovenfresh Industries
will make you the new face
of Auntie Ovenfresh.
C'mon, Marge.
It's either you, or...
I guess it would be a hoot
to have my face on everything.
Oh, Mrs. Simpson,
you must pursue your dreams.
Like my old dream
of coming to America
and starting a family.
Or my new dream
of ditching my family
and sneaking back
to India in disguise.
Apu? Never heard of him.
My name is Steve Barnes.
(instrumental music playing)
So, when do they
start singing?
Well, The Playdude Advisor
says this music
will get a stewardess
to give you a layover.
I hope it's in Omaha.
My grammy lives there.
MARGE:
Bart, can you come in here
for a second?
Your mother's about
to show us her new recipe.
Outta sight!
Lay it on me, Mama.
In the Ovenfresh Bakeoff,
clever presentation
is as important as taste.
So I'm entering
my dessert dogs!
It's deep-fried cookie dough
with meringue buns,
cherry "ketchup"
and caramel "mustard."
Mmm! It's dessert,
but it's hot dogs,
so it's good for you!
Marge, I don't want
to freak you out,
but I think I love you.
I hope the Ovenfresh Bakeoff
likes them as much as you do.
Mom, a letter
from Ovenfresh Industries!
Well, open it.
Open it! Open it!
"Thank you for applying
to the Ovenfresh Bakeoff.
Every year many wonderful cooks
fail to qualify."
(sighs)
"...but screw them, you're in!
Congratulations!"
Oh, my God!
Someone somewhere says
I'm better than someone else!
I'm proud of you, honey.
(sobbing)
Sorry, Ralphie.
The Bakeoff
rejected your recipe.
I wanna be in the bakeoff!
There, there.
I think your grilled
crayon sandwich was delicious.
You only had a pretend bite.
No, I'm eating it.
Look.
Mmm.
Can you taste
the thumbtacks?
Uh, crap.
I'm here live at the annual
Ovenfresh Bakeoff,
brought to you
by the Ovenfresh Flour
family of products,
including...
Quetzalcoatl's Choice:
the favorite from Zihuatanejo
to Popocatepetl.
Ha-ha! Bart looks
different today.
Ah, Nelson,
your debonair wit
reminds me
of a young Mort Sahl.
Guh?
Listen up,
ring-a-ding-dingers.
I'm throwin'
a little sip 'n' quip
at the Playdude Treehouse
Saturday night
at the top of the ladder.
Be there or be square.
(chattering)
I want to be
a triangle.
You're not invited.
It's going to be weird
cooking
without your tipsy father
grabbing me from behind,
but I think I'm up to it.
Welcome to the
Ovenfresh Bakeoff.
I'm Billy Bouillon Cube.
Follow me
to your oven station.
Why, thank you, Billy.
Don't look
at my human eyes!
Oh, don't mind Billy.
His oven light's on,
but nothing's cooking.
(chuckles)
So, what you makin'...
Marge?
Well... Stuart,
I'm making a dessert
that looks like a hot dog,
but it isn't.
You're making a "tasty fake"?
(chuckles):
That is so '90s.
Why don't we all move to Seattle
and use slow modems?
(laughter)
Yo, Marge, your recipe--
she is pathetic.
She is not!
(playing jazz music)
Great licks, man, great licks.
Yo, Bart, there's no room
left in the grotto.
Who's that adult?
Hey, it wouldn't be a Playdude
party without James Caan.
So, I'm trying to talk
with Miss November,
and Charlie Callas over here
is blocking my action with...
(hooting like Charlie Callas)
Turns out he's choking
on a peanut.
Well, a punch to the gut
cleared that right up.
(kids laughing)
Bart, me and Mrs. Krabappel--
uh, we're going to go play
some "backgammon,"
if you know what I mean.
I don't,
but I hope you win.
Oh, he's going to win.
Some guys like a challenge.
Not me.
Ladies and gentlemen,
before we begin, let us
introduce Auntie Ovenfresh,
1954!
Ribbons and trophies
are no comfort on your deathbed.
Auntie Ovenfresh!
(chuckling)
And now, chefs,
start your kitchens!
(gasps)
Hmm? Fish scales?
Stop! You're
tainting my entry!
Oh, I'm-a so sorry.
It was, uh,
how you say, um,
"done with malice
aforethought," yes?
You did it on purpose?
No, no, no, no, no, no,
my English--
she's a-not-a so good.
I was, uh, how you say, uh,
uh, "ruining your food
so I win," yes?
(sighs):
Why is everyone
at this bakeoff
such a meanie-bo-beanie?
These muffin-huffin'
batter biddies
can smell weakness
a mile away...
weakness named Marge!
Why can't everyone
just play fair and...?
Did you just dunk your hair
in my mixing bowl?
You're weak, weak!
CHIEF WIGGUM:
Listen here, Simpson.
Your son has been exposing
our kids
to adult themes,
unabashed dictionaries
and the lesser short fiction
of John Cheever.
Adult themes?
What are you talking about?
My Roddy told a joke
about an octopus
and a set of bagpipes,
and the punch line implied
that they fornicated!
Ralphie wants to go
on the pill!
Stupid Bart.
(laughing):
Bagpipes getting down
with an octopus.
That's classic.
Hot bananas
coming through.
-Oops.
-(screams)
(gasps):
My dessert!
(shrieking)
(sobbing)
Come on, Mom.
You still have 20 minutes left.
You can fix it.
You're right.
If I can feed a family of five
on $12 a week,
I can do anything.
You feed us
on $12 a week?
I stretch your father's
meatloaf with sawdust.
Attention,
contestants,
baking time is over.
The judging will commence
in one hour.
If your dish
is not in the judging room
by the time this metal door
hits the ground,
your entry will not be official
and will be eaten
by the janitor.
(beeps)
Hurry, Mom!
Whew! I guess
I was the last one.
-(metal clanging)
-Damn it!
(thuds)
These other dishes look
so pretty.
And those cheaters blackened
my sugar wieners.
I'd like to give
those Betty Crookeds
a taste of their own medicine.
Yes... medicine.
Baby ear medicine.
(laughing)
(groans)
Even the Pope couldn't
forgive this pizza,
and he's letting a lot
of things slide these days.
Don't worry.
There's plenty for all of you.
Now who's laughing, huh, huh?
(laughing)
Me! I'm laughing!
I can't believe
my mom would cheat.
Hey, sweetie,
is Mom winning?
Oh, she'll win
the contest,
but she'll lose her soul.
But she'll still win
the contest?
And lose her soul.
But win the contest?
-Yes.
-Whoo-hoo!
If Marge becomes
Auntie Ovenfresh,
we'll meet all
the food personalities...
Look!
It's Mr. Cashew,
the Koobler Dwarfs,
Snip, Crinkle
and Poof...
Twinkle the Kidd,
I love you!
(grunts)
Whoa-ho-ho,
easy there, partner.
(dying gurgle)
Uh-oh.
You... killed him.
He was my world!
ALL (chanting):
Blood for creme!
Blood for creme.
It's always difficult
to pick two finalists,
but this year it was easy.
All the other dishes
made us vomit.
(gagging)
Our two remaining dishes are
"Blackened Dessert Dogs"
by Marge Simpson
and "Armadillo a la Road"
by Brandine
No Last Name Given.
That's an entry?!
I thought it was garbage.
Just 'cause it was cooked
in a garbage can
don't make it garbage.
(laughs)
(groans)
"Canned and frozen juices
are more popular
than ever these days...
but most bachelors we know
would prefer to squeeze
their own tomatoes."
(laughing)
Bachelors are always
squeezin' stuff.
Would you excuse us,
Milton?
It's Milhouse.
Yeah, and your father's
"No House". Now scram.
Aw...
Maybe I was a
little hard on him.
Oh, well. Bart, I know
a father has no right
to pry into the life
of his ten-year-old son,
-but what's going
on up here?
-I'm just spreadin'
the Playdude philosophy:
hi-fis, Norman Mailer,
gettin' some...
Uh, um... what do
you think "some" is?
Uh... Toys?
(sighs):
I thought I'd never
have to do this,
but it's time to tell
you the facts of life.
Do you know
what a boob is?
Oh, yeah.
Good, that'll save us
some time. Okay.
Why do you think your mother
and I sleep in the same bed?
Because we're poor?
Exactly, and we're poor
because we have kids.
And the biological method
by which children are created
by a man
and a woman is...
(Bart screams)
BART:
And then the man...
(Bart and Milhouse scream)
BART AND MILHOUSE:
And then the woman...
(Bart, Milhouse,
Uter, and Martin scream)
(kids screaming)
Well, it's better
they hear it from me now
than from their parents
when they're old enough.
Congratulations, Mom.
You seem to have a prescription
for success.
What a kind yet oddly ominous
thing to say.
Now I've got to get ready
for the finals.
Don't forget
your secret ingredient...
cheating!
Well, it's
not my fault!
Lisa, the people
in this bakeoff
are stinkers who pushed me
and pushed me
like the pushy-wushies
they are!
Mom, if I don't have you
to look up to,
I don't have anyone.
Look, I'll be a winner
with feet of clay...
like Mickey Mantle.
Everyone loves the Mick.
I don't want
Mickey Mantle.
I want my mom.
Hey, plenty of kids
are going to look up to me
when I'm Auntie...
whatever it is.
Right now, people just know me
as the wife of a guy
who doesn't go to work.
Can't you understand
that I need this?
(sighs):
I guess Dad has to be
my hero now.
Not if you knew
what he's been doing.
Welcome to
the final battle
of the Ovenfresh Challenge.
Ooh, she's already ahead of me.
Well, I didn't come this far
not to cheat.
Huh?
"I look up to you...
because you let me down."
That's clever...
and devastating.
Hmm...
Stop the competition!
AUDIENCE:
Wha...?!
I don't deserve to win.
I sabotaged
all the other entries.
(audience gasping)
Looks like me and Marge
are both going to hell.
That's when I'll make my move.
Then I won... with my festive
holiday Alco-Hog.
Huh. I thought
it was dead.
(moaning)
Thanks, honey,
for saving me from myself.
And Marge, you'll always be
the best chef in our house.
Eh, B.F.D.
I've had your
scrambled eggs, Homer.
The secret ingredient
is whiskey.
Hey, it keeps
the kids quiet.
Hey, look!
The new Ovenfresh Flour bag!
Yeah, that could've been me.
CLETUS:
Oh, I wish
it had've been.
(whimpers)
Now that Brandine's famous,
she done run off
with James Caan!
But don't you worry.
I'm going to fix his wagon.
A toll booth?
I hate these things.
That's it.
Next time, I fly.
Shh!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem