CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(theme music stops abruptly)
What? Can't we sit
on the couch without
something happening?
D'oh!
♪♪
I can't believe Mr. Burns
reserved the entire museum
just for an office party.
It doesn't seem fair
to the regular visitors.
We drove 18 hours to come here.
On the plus side,
this rope is mighty soft.
Mm. Touch it, kids.
Par-ty! Par-ty!
Homer, these are people
you work with.
Show some restraint.
Re-straint! Re-straint!
Re-straint!
(loud wolf howl)
(groaning)
Lighten up, Marge.
This is my chance to relax
with people from work
I never get to see.
Like this guy.
I'm your supervisor!
Really? How am I doing?
(scoffs)
Well, well, if it isn't
my favorite employee
and his spouse.
And these must be children.
Have a ginger root.
Mr. Burns acting nice?
That's odd.
He must be up
to something.
Lis, Mr. Burns is the
sweetest, kindest man I know.
How many men
do you know?
Basically, him and Dad.
Nice tux, Moe.
Yeah, thanks.
I bought this
for my funeral.
It ain't got no
back, so don't
make me turn around.
Hmm.
Hey, I'm paying for
a silk-lined coffin,
and damn it,
I'm going to feel it!
NARRATOR (on video):
Since the dawn of aviation,
man has built museums
dedicated to the history
of flight,
and created audio-visual
materials to orient visitors
to those museums.
From the hand-drawn flip book a
the Wright Brothers' Museum
to the IMAX movie
at Cape Canaveral,
aviation museum audio-visual
materials have taken
patrons and docents alike on
a rocket ride to comprehension.
This...is the story
of those materials.
Hey, it's a guy
in a goofy Burns head!
Act like Burns!
(laughing)
That's him to a T!
Here we have a vintage film
of the original
Springfield Wing Walkers,
including our own Agnes Skinner.
♪♪
(cows mooing)
(clapping)
HOMER:
Wow, a wooden plane.
It's about time trees were
good for something,
instead of just standing there
like jerks.
"The Plywood Pelican
was larger than
a football field.
It weighs more than
the state of New Hampshire.
It was only flown once,
by its creator,
Mr. C. Montgomery Burns."
I flew it at an
altitude of six feet
for a distance
of four-and-a-half feet.
Then we discovered
rain makes it catch fire.
Then the Fuhrer fired me.
What a magical party
this has been.
Mr. Burns is a great man.
I've got a bad feeling
about all of this.
Come on, Marge.
This place is great.
Free admission, great grub
and we got to use
the bathroom of the future.
Homer, that was Apollo 12!
Greetings, wage-donkeys.
Is everyone happy and content?
LENNY:
Yeah!
CARL:
This is great!
I would die for you!
Is your sense of outrage dulled?
Spill it, Super-boss!
(chuckles)
Very well...
effective immediately,
the employee prescription
drug program is terminated.
(gasping)
-What?
-Why?
In these days
of rising health care costs...
blah, blah, blah... lip service,
lip service... get out!
This must be
the "nasty surprise"
he mentioned
in the invitation.
(angry shouting)
-This sucks!
-Get him!
Fly, you fool!
I tried to explain
to you, sir,
this thing has never
actually worked.
Smithers... you must believe.
(Smithers grunting,
pedals squeaking)
(angry shouting)
BURNS:
Next stop, Pirate Island.
(pedals squeaking)
Well, that was
a pretty good party.
Do you think Carol from payroll
and Mike from shipping
are going to hook up?
(panting):
He's married.
Change course!
Carol must be warned!
Now that Mr. Burns has
eliminated the drug plan,
we're gonna have
to cut back on our diseases.
I'll get a second job,
one that pays well.
You think those
guys on Friends
need another friend?
That show's gone off the air.
Damn it! I would've been perfect
as Rachel's Irish cousin.
(Irish accent):
So you're all doing
each other, are ya?
Well, who's going
to put out for old Seamus?
I need a new job
that provides
-full health benefits.
-Uh-huh.
As long as I only
work five hours a day.
No heavy lifting,
no light clerical,
none of that secret
Santa crap.
Tasteful nudity.
Uh, well, let me
see what I've got.
You have defeated
the doom-bot
and sealed the portal.
Phobos is safe.
Phobos? That's
a good job for me.
Following the lead
of Springfield Nuclear Power,
other local companies
are canceling
their prescription drug plans..
even here at Channel Six!
Now, kids, I want you to go to
your parents' medicine cabinet,
and find all the pills
labeled "Lithium Dibromide,"
and send them to me-- now!
No one likes a bipolar clown.
(laughing)
(crying)
To cope with the crisis,
many consumers
are turning to alternative
forms of treatment.
I've had to
medicate Ralphie
with stuff from
the evidence locker.
(laughs)
I'm cuckoo for contraband.
Of course, this
wouldn't be necessary
if retail drug prices
were reasonable.
Dr. Julius Hibbert,
do you agree?
Well, now, Kent,
give the drug companies a break
They have lots of hidden costs
and they know
how to treat a brother.
Let me introduce you to the
fine-lookin' females of Pfizer.
♪ I like big butts
and I cannot lie ♪
♪ You other brothers
can't deny ♪
♪ That when a girl walks in
with an itty-bitty waist ♪
♪ And a round thing in your
face, you get sprung... ♪
(music playing)
Possible side effects
include dizziness
and shortness of marriage.
Damn.
MAN:
Well, let me start out
by saying that it is
always a pleasure
to sit down with
a mother and a daughter
who have snuck past Security
and burst into my office.
I just don't see why one
little pill should cost $30.
Drugs aren't so expensive
in other countries.
In other countries,
families also lie
on the floor
and eat bugs.
What countries
are those?
You ever been to Norway?
-No.
-Well, they do
it in Norway,
and that's why
I personally thank God
we pay too much for drugs.
I mean, uh, the right amount.
I mean, not enough.
Here, watch this video.
(new age music)
NARRATOR:
The mighty Amazon River.
The natives had a word for it.
Then we got rid of the natives
and no one remembers that word,
but, here are some words
everyone remembers,
by Huey Lewis and the News.
♪ I want a new drug ♪
♪ One that won't make me sick ♪
♪ One that won't
make me crash my car ♪
♪ Or make me feel
three feet thick ♪
♪ I want a new drug ♪
♪ One that won't
hurt my head... ♪
(men coughing)
All right,
here's your medication.
Wait a minute.
This ain't no pill.
It's a corn nut.
I got a bottle cap.
(buzzing)
Mine flew away.
Let me explain
from behind this cage.
Now, your pills have
become very expensive
and no one gives
a rat's ass about you,
so after a lot of
thought, we decided
to let you go cold turkey.
For those of you
who survive the night,
we'll be having
waffles tomorrow.
Ooh, waffles!
I didn't die
in World War II
just to be pushed around by
some pill-hoarding hussy!
I'm gonna fight this thing.
He's crazy, but what
are you gonna do?
He's young.
MARGE:
Well, the drug company
won't do anything
to help us.
I got the answer!
Dad?
Oh, thank God,
it's the right place.
I burst into four
homes before this one.
Now, listen.
All the drugs we want
are right across the border.
I have a friend who'll help us.
The border, eh?
Then I'd better
sand off my fingerprints.
(yelling)
I could just wear gloves.
Nah, they're upstairs.
(yelling, moaning)
Hola, señor.
We are gringos who wish to spend
mucho dinero in your country.
Splendid.
Welcome to Canada.
D'oh!
Okay, Abe, here are your
fake Canadian health cards.
Take them
to any pharmacy
and you'll
get enough drugs
to make Regina
look like Saskatoon.
(all laughing)
That's a good
one, Johnny.
Thanks a million, Johnny.
In appreciation,
I'd like to give you
this DVD player.
What the heck?
Where do you pour the syrup?
I'd like some Vioxx,
Cumadin, Albuterol,
Prevacid and an auto-inflate
blood-pressure-monitor C-cuff,
with case.
Anything you like,
fellow Canadian.
Canadian?!
Them's fightin' words!
I mean, accurate words.
♪ One pill makes you larger ♪
♪ And one pill makes you small
♪ And the ones
that mother gives you ♪
♪ Don't do anything at all ♪
♪ Go ask Alice ♪
♪ When she's ten feet tall ♪
Anything to declare?
I declare
that you have
the most beautiful
brown eyes.
Why I do believe you're
smuggling...
a heart as big as all outdoors.
Now get in my
country, ya big lug.
(sneaky chuckles)
Did he have a passport?
Yes... to my heart.
(singsongy)
Drugs! Various drugs!
Be sure
to read instructions!
Uh-oh! Where'd
I put the instructions?
Now, who's next?
I got pills to make
you sleep late,
coagulate,
eliminate and copulate...
in that order.
Grampa.
We would like to thank you
for all you have
done for us.
Please accept this Operation
Dumbo Drop souvenir jacket.
Look. They used the same "D"
for "Dumbo" and "Drop."
Ha! Unbelievably, only three
were ever purchased.
Marge?
Bart?
Lisa?
(ukulele playing)
Aloha!
Wow, this is
just like Hawaii,
but you don't
get beaten up
if you leave the
hotel. What gives?
We just wanted
to thank you.
Because of the Xanax,
I'm not over-anxious
about being
a Simpson anymore.
I am a little anxious
about being on Xanax,
but the Zoloft
covers that nicely.
My Dad, the drug mule.
(gagging)
Uh. Ew.
Oh, man, I need something
to settle my stomach.
Oh, wait. I was supposed
to take these with food.
Oh, look, it is Mr. Homer,
my favorite customer.
Please-- feel free to
paw through my Playdudes
and tell me to go back
to some country I am
not actually from.
Why the sweet talk, Apu?
Are you after some cheap drugs?
Please let me come on one
of your smuggling runs!
My eight babies
are driving me crazy
with their coughing and sneezing
and general oozing, and...
My Janitor in a Drum
is afraid to come out.
What does that mean?
I don't even know.
That's the kind
of bad joke
I am making,
I am so tired.
Help me out, Homer.
My little Roddy
needs his insulin.
Breaks my heart to watch him
jones-diddly-ownsing.
Flanders?
I don't know.
I mean, you haven't
done anything for me
since you lent me that
5,000 bucks yesterday.
I don't claim to be
the perfect neighbor.
If you let us come,
I will give you
ten minutes alone with
my Squishee machine.
Do what you will.
No cameras?
(sputtering)
No cameras.
Homer,
tell Mr. Ned
to stop trying to convert me!
I was just telling him how brave
he is to worship a false god.
I do not worship one god, okay?
I worship a whole super-team
of deities that...
Ow! Ow! Okay,
he just pinched me!
Well, where's
your super-team now?
Listen, you two,
I'll tell you who
the true God is
if you're both quiet
the rest of the trip!
-But the infinite beauty...
-But the Bible says...
All right,
I'm comin' back there.
APU:
Save me, Shiva!
FLANDERS: Why don't
you just call out for Hawk Man?
APU: Why don't you shut up?
Well circle-cut my bacon!
Look at all these
Yankee-doodly-dandies!
Is there another Vietnam
going on?
Hello, neighborino
to the north.
I sure like the cut
of your gibberish.
Co-indodlie-diddly.
Diddly-oodly
Oodly...
Piccadooddly.
oodly-oodly...
Noodly-daddly-
diddly-daddly.
Diddly-daddly-utner...
Loony-oodly.
Maple-iddly.
Doodly-doddly-diddly,
doddly.
Say, would you like
to puff on a reefer-ino?
It's legal here!
They warned me
Satan would be attractive.
Let's go.
Anyone want some coffee
for the ride back?
It's not that convenience
store crap, is it?
Because I don't feed
that to my dogs.
No, no, it's home-brewed.
Careful, it's hotter
than a Fox News
weather skank.
Ooh, my, hot, hot, hot!
La, la, la, la, la, la, la!
Here, let me wrap
this wet towel
around your head
to cool you off.
La-la-la-la-la-la-la!
Ha! Ha!
La-la-la-la! Ha! Ha!
La-la-la-la!
Stop him!
He's expressing
his faith, eh!
(guns cocking)
Hold on.
We're just innocent tourists.
(guns cocking)
La-la-la-la-la-la-la!
I took another sip.
Today, Mounties busted a major
American drug smuggling ring.
Former U.S. astronaut
Homer Simpson
was taken into custody.
Oh, my butt looks so huge
during perp walks.
We've confiscated your car
and its contents.
(translating):
Nous avons confisque
votre voiture
et ses contenus.
You may leave Canada,
but never return.
Vous etes permis de quitter
le Canada,
mais vous n'avez pas
le droit de rentrer.
I am a big fat
French idiot.
Je suis un grand
gros... hey!
(chuckles)
No more drugs.
We let everyone down.
Your jacket, señor.
Thank God we did not stitch
your name over the breast.
(sighs)
Dad, you tried your best.
For the first time
in my life
I can say
without being drunk,
that I truly admire you.
BOTH:
Aw...
No drinking in public!
Hey, where'd it go?
Oh, well.
Ah, there's nothing like
canceling an employee drug plan
to make one feel so at peace
with the universe.
I agree, sir.
Shut up.
I'm so sick of you, Smithers.
Your toadying,
your complete agreeability,
your gasping on the floor...
Wha?!
Smithers, if this
is some sort of hijink,
stop it immediately.
Sir, my thyroid
is swelling up.
Confound it, man!
I need your throat clear
and ready for perjury.
When you canceled the drug plan,
I couldn't afford
my Thyroxin anymore.
But before I die,
there are words
I've always longed to say.
Sir, I...
(choking noises)
Fear not, Smithers.
I'll move Heaven
and Earth to save you!
It's still easier
than teaching
a new assistant
my filing system.
I just wish we could
make one last big score.
But we could never drive
past the border patrol.
There are other ways
to get into Canada...
(screams)
That's it, a plane!
Smuggle drugs
in a plane?
That'll never work!
Sure it will.
All we need is a pilot!
BURNS:
I've got everything you need.
HOMER:
Katharine Hepburn?!
No, you fool.
'Tis I, Burns!
Now come with me.
BURNS: At last,
my plane shall be used
for its original purpose--
to subvert the laws
of the United States.
Looks like your plane's
pretty full, eh?
Don't wanna overload it.
(scoffs):
Typical Canadian wimpiness.
That's why you have snowballs
and we have the H-bomb.
We really appreciate
your help, Johnny.
Is there any way
we can repay you?
Well, I've always wanted
to see a man
with the IQ of a child
executed by the state.
We don't get that
up here.
Really? In America,
we do it four times
a week.
You come on down,
and I'll get us
front row seats.
I'd like that.
We're losing altitude.
Time to dump
all unnecessary weight.
Wha...? Don't dump me out!
I can lose weight!
Just give me a chance.
One... two...
Eh, I'd rather die.
It's no use.
We've got to make
an emergency landing.
Well, at least we're all
in this together.
Now, we have three parachutes.
This one's for me...
And these two are gifts
for my nephews.
Tally ho!
(gasping)
ABE:
Homer, are you sure
you can fly this thing?
We'll make it, Dad.
On a wing and a prayer.
Damn it!
(snoring)
(gasps)
(sirens wailing)
(gun cocks)
All right,
you're under arrest.
On what charge?
Making a police chief go...
(gasps)
Get in the car.
And don't touch those guns.
I just loaded them.
You'll have
to arrest me, too.
Abe Simpson brought
the Propecia
to keep grass on Willie's field.
He cured my lumbago. Thank you.
My diaper rash.
My glayvinoids
are not so hurtful!
Thanks to his lactose-
intolerance pills,
I can drink this
Krusty-brand milkshake.
Terrible!
Well, Simpson,
you have helped
a lot of people,
so, like it says
in the Springfield
Police Handbook,
"If you can't beat 'em,
join 'em."
(cheering)
Uh, Chief, you know,
I've been checkin'
the handbook.
A lot of the things you say
aren't in there at all.
Yeah, well, look
a little closer, Lou.
(cheering)
(panting)
Oh, I hope I'm not too late.
Take, potion! Hurry!
Oh, it's not working.
Only my sour, curdled breath
will quicken him.
(grunting)
(pleasant groan)
(groans)
(sighs)
Ah!
Sir, you saved my life!
Yes. Smithers, I was
a stingy old fool.
But from now on,
I'll provide drug benefits
to all my full-time employees.
Great news, honey!
Mr. Burns made me
a freelance consultant!
Hey...
what's this lump?
Shh!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem