ANNOUNCER: We now return
to Keepin' It Kodos,
starring Kang.
Is dinner ready yet?
Our boss will be here
any minute now.
(canned laughter)
(shrieking)
Ugh! This one
keeps eating himself.
MARGE: Hello?
Octopuses, I'm done.
Am I the only one here
who's in horrible pain?
You're the only one
who won't shut up about it.
MALE ALIEN: Mmm.
What a delicious meal.
I feel like
I'm going to burst.
Cool! I'm vomit!
(chuckles):
Well, a fine meal
like that
deserves a hyper-
galactic promotion.
BOTH:
Hyper-galactic!
Wait a minute.
I don't have a family anymore.
You do now, Son.
You do now.
♪ Standing tall ♪
♪ On the wings of my dreams ♪
♪ Rise and fall ♪
♪ The rain and thunder... ♪
(Homer grunts)
(grunting)
(cat yowls)
Homer,
what are you doing?
Trying to get a Frisbee
off the roof.
(grunts)
Ow!
Ah, there's the Frisbee.
(chuckles)
(Flanders groaning weakly)
Concussion, diddily,
hemorrhage, doodily,
injury, bodily.
Ned, you nearly died...
of a brain tumor.
Thank goodness
that bowling ball
knocked it out of your head.
(laughs):
Welcome back, dawg.
(yelling)
-(gasps)
-My, you look
awfully pale.
Let's get you some fresh air.
Hey, while you're there, can you
get my Frisbee off the ledge?
All right, but I swear to God,
this is the very last time.
(grunts)
(shouts)
Oh, man, is this going to hurt.
(relieved sigh)
That's better.
(laughing)
Ooh!
Come on, Ned.
Just because you foresaw
Dr. Hibbert's death
doesn't mean you can see
into the future.
It was just a sinister
co-inky-dink.
Help me!
Some bullies
threw my shoes
over a telephone wire...
with me in them!
Just wriggle loose.
I'll catch you,
li'l critter.
(shrieks)
(screaming)
Oh, another setback.
What the Family Circus?
A second premonition
came to fruition.
Lord, why have you given me
these unholy visions of doom?
(gasps)
Well, I didn't need any special
power to know that was coming.
Hey, Flanders,
have you seen my Frisbee?
Homer, I can foretell
people's deaths.
People's deaths, eh?
-(barking)
-(yowling)
Do me! Do me!
(sighs)
(shouting)
(gasping)
So, what'd I die of?
Too much happiness?
Naked girl avalanche?
Uh, you die eating
a submarine sandwich.
What kind of bread?
Um, country parmesan.
Whoo-hoo!
Mr. Flanders,
why are you moving?
'Cause I had a vision of myself
shooting your father.
In this neighborhood,
who hasn't?
Well, you can't
fight fate,
but if you must shoot
our father,
please remember
our family motto:
"Not in the face."
Don't worry, sweetie.
I am not going to kill
your father.
Flanders? Kill me?
(laughing)
You never
killed anybody,
and you're going to start
with the big dog?
Homer, please,
don't tempt the gods.
I-I mean God.
There's-there's one God!
Only one!
Well, sometimes there's three.
Hey, Chief,
throw me your piece.
Uh, sure thing, citizen.
Come on. Shoot me a new one.
Ooh, I'm so scared!
Ned Flanders is pointing
a gun at me.
You couldn't even shoot me
by accident,
even if I whacked the barrel
like this.
Quit whacking my barrel!
Never!
(grunts):
You leave me no choice!
(sighs)
I was supposed to shoot you,
but I didn't;
I changed the future!
What have I done?
I've changed the future
for the worse.
Homer, stay away
from the nuclear plant.
Fine, I'll
never go back...
starting tomorrow.
Today is Lenny's birthday,
and they're having
ice cream cake.
But-but you're going
to kill us all!
But ice cream cake!
(tires screeching)
(crow caws)
I got to find Homer.
He's going to blow up
the whole town!
Yeah, well, you know,
you got to take the bitter
with the sweet.
(muted):
Homer! Homer!
Homer, do not press
the core destruct button!
(with radio static):
Press... destruct button.
Don't do it! Don't do it!
You'll kill everyone!
(radio static):
Do it... do it!
Kill everyone!
Sure is taking me a long time
to reach this button.
Must...
...kill...
...best friend.
(shouting)
(scoffs):
Homer, fall backward!
(sighs):
Whew!
(grunting)
(sighs):
Whew!
Oh, you stupid son of a...
Homer, I'm so mad at you!
I'll bet you blew up
the town
just to get out
of cleaning the garage.
(chuckling)
Everything's coming up Homer.
Yeah, well, the joke's
on you, smart guy.
The garage made it
to Heaven, too.
Hmm, I wonder
if I could blow up Heaven?
GOD:
Homer Simpson, it's time
you got what's coming to you.
Your Frisbee.
Cool. You guys got
a good buffet up here?
Oh, yeah. Just stay away
from the three-bean salad.
-You're not
the boss of me.
-(groans)
♪♪
(hoofbeats galloping)
(horse neighing)
Hello, ducky.
(screaming)
(Cockney accent):
You gave me quite
a fright, you did.
Say, you don't need
no fancy knife
to get me attention,
not with those
handsome muttonchops.
Come on.
Give us a snog.
(grunts)
That's not a snog.
Looks like the Muttonchop
Murderer has struck again.
What should we do
with the body?
I want you to dust her
for prints.
What does that mean?
The Prince is coming by,
and I want her clean
when he looks her over.
Perhaps we can be of assistance,
Inspector.
Well, well, well,
look who's here.
Master detective
Eliza Simpson
and her easily amazed sidekick,
Dr. Bartley.
(gasps):
What's this?
A doorknob. Good show.
So, what clues
has the body shewn?
We don't need clues.
We've already
caught the killer.
Oh, eh, please?
This mysterious Hindu
is clearly responsible
for the murder.
Lock him up till we find
someone darker, boys.
Please, I am not a killer.
I am but a humble purveyor
of disgusting British food.
Lark tongues, head pudding,
eel pies.
Eel pie?
My favorite.
Mmm... (laughs)
We British
sure eat crap.
Inspector,
might I have a word wit' you?
Absolutely.
(gagging)
-Get back down there, you.
-(eel squeaks)
(grunting)
(gulping)
You were saying?
Well, it's like this.
I'm a proper Cockney
flower girl, I am,
and I sees this
real strange bloke.
Out of sorts.
Mad in the eyes.
-All kettles and biscuits.
-Right.
-Well, he seen I was
lookin' at him,
-Mm-hmm.
and he drops this and runs.
Cor, blimey, skip to me loo.
Good Lord.
I'm afraid this case is beyond
even your powers, little girl.
I'll take that challenge,
Inspector.
Yeah, well, good luck.
Uh, now, boys,
let's see the suspect
in that child abduction case.
I shall never grow up.
Uh, in jail you will.
Yes, I recognize this blade.
I sold it as part of a set--
the famed
Seven Swords of Osiris.
Now would you be interested
in an illustrated novelette?
It also includes a "Young
David Diligent" adventure.
Confound it, man!
I need to know
who bought those swords!
Very well.
I will check my records.
You may examine my curios,
but do not touch my oddities.
Use your judgment
with my gewgaws.
Well, I'll be blazed.
I know these missionaries.
I just told the natives they
were having sex the wrong way.
Help! Help!
Murther!
The Muttonchop Murderer
is long gone.
But this ledger
will lead us to him.
(groans)
This potion
will give me new life.
(straining)
I'm alive.
I'm gonna go to America.
I'll be in pictures.
You'll see.
The whole world is gonna know
the name Simon Stoolowitz.
It says here
the swords were sold
to C. Ebenezer Burns.
Burns?
The evil industrialist
who makes coal
out of babies?
I know just
where to find him.
Ebenezer Burns?
Yeah, he's over here.
How ya doin', there?
Fresh'n your pipe?
Anybody need a let-me-down?
Whoa, whoa,
heads up there, buddy.
A rat's gnawin' off your toe.
The Sword of Osiris.
I once possessed
the entire collection.
Then I sold them
all for opium.
Oh, how I wish
I had them back...
to sell for more opium.
Who did you sell
the swords to?
A fat man
with sideburns...
like that one over there.
(gasps)
There's
your Muttonchop Murderer!
Stop, fiend!
(grunting)
Opium rules.
Hey, hey.
Read the sign.
Well, well,
what have we here?
Inspector, you've
caught the villain!
But what are you doing
in an opium den?
It's the only way I can
get Ralphie to go to sleep.
I can make "opi-ohs."
Well, Dr. Bartley, another
mystery well solved.
Yes, with the murderer
behind bars,
London's working girls
are free to follow
their merry calling.
(both gasping)
Yet another
Sword of Osiris.
But that must mean...
the murderer is still at large.
Ah, he could have killed
this one days ago.
The body is bloated,
and the face is rotten.
(grunts)
It was five minutes ago,
you twit.
(groans)
(sniffing)
Hmm...
(crowd chattering excitedly)
Please spare me.
I'm not a murderer. I'm not.
And I've never known
the pleasures of a woman...
or a proper eating apple.
Quiet, you.
(munching)
Yuck.
There's cheese in my eel pie.
This week,
in our Summer Hanging Series,
we're pleased
to present
the Muttonchop
Murderer.
At last God-fearing Londoners
are free to walk Whore Alley.
Stay your hand,
Inspector.
That man is innocent.
The murderer's blade
is covered with blood,
but the handle is covered
with something else:
the unmistakable fragrance
of eel pie.
Hey, lots of people
like eel pie.
Yeah? Well, how many of them
have muttonchops?
(crowd gasping)
Why can't you be
more like Eddie?
He never says
a word against me.
That's 'cause
you cut out his tongue.
E's 'ight, 'eef.
Inspector Wiggum,
you were the most famous
member of Scotland Yard.
Why would you do this?
Well, the fact is,
I wanted to come up with a case
even you couldn't solve.
And besides...
so long,
you stupid British twits!
You'll never catch me.
I'm traveling
at the speed of wind.
(laughing)
Remember me for my police work
and not the murders!
Well done.
Their fleet is destroyed.
(both laughing)
Daddy,
I had the craziest dream.
Ralphie,
you're still in it.
(bird squawking)
Whee!
♪♪
(speaking gibberish)
PLEASANT FEMALE VOICE:
I have a serious brain disease.
Please give me a cat.
(speaking gibberish
affirmatively)
This comically
large capsule
has lifetime supplies
of niacin, thiamin,
and riboflavin-glavin.
(excited murmuring)
(excited giggling)
Prior to ingestion,
the pill must be reduced
by my amazing
new shrink ray.
Pfft. Shrink ray?
Oh, there's always
something else to buy.
First I lower the capsule top,
thusly...
Then I zap the capsule,
"thisly"...
And now, who would like
a lifetime
of perfect health?
I'll take it.
No, no that's now...
well, all right.
(faint sucking noise)
That sounds
like Maggie.
But she's right here...
(shrieks)
Now, now don't worry,
my dear woman.
She will be rocked gently
to sleep by the stomach acid.
(shrieks)
(happily giggling)
Hold on, Maggie!
Daddy's coming!
(grunting):
Come on. Get...
I've got her!
Oh, Mag...
No, wait. This is yours.
(gulps)
Your daughter
has 30 minutes
before the acid
dissolves
the capsule.
But we can rescue her
by sending
a miniaturized vessel
through
Mr. Burns' body.
Ooh, stop that!
The felt is slicing
through me like a knife.
Bionauts assemble!
Captain!
Science Officer!
Security!
Marge!
Now, I insist you take off
your shoes when you get inside.
And, uh,
while you're in there,
grab as much cancer
as you can.
Let the commencement
"beginulate"!
(groans)
Now, you must enter
the subclavian vein.
Screw you, doc!
I fly from the gut.
Dad, you should
listen to him.
He's a man
of science
and you can barely read.
Bah!
Has science ever kissed a woman
or won the Super Bowl
or put a man on the moon?
This is what I think
of your precious science.
(grunting)
(yelling)
Help me, science!
Your ship is wedged
in Mr. Burns' heart.
And you must dislodge it
from outside.
But watch out for retroviruses.
Oh, boy, are they retro.
It's a fun design by R. Crumb,
who was friends
with Harvey Pekar.
Seriously though,
touch one and you're dead.
Why is my swimsuit so revealing?
Marge, that's
what turns
a mediocre voyage
into a fantastic voyage.
(growls)
(grunting)
Maybe this'll help.
Where'd you get that rib?
There's a whole rack
of 'em over there.
I only ate two.
(grunting)
Bart, what are
you doing?
Takin' a whiz.
Stop that!
We're guests
in Mr. Burns.
To get to Maggie
in time,
we'll have to catch a ride
on a nerve impulse--
the body's information
superhighway.
Learning is cool!
(cheering)
And to make sure
we get there super fast,
I'm hitting all the buttons
with my palm.
(grunts)
(siren blaring)
(explosion)
Well, that hurt like hell.
My sweet,
undigested baby!
(happy giggling)
(engine sputtering)
I'm afraid I have
some bad news, uh, Simpsons.
With the baby's extra weight,
you don't have enough power
to make it back,
and one of you must stay
behind to save the rest.
Frink out.
Oh, my God!
This is the worst Halloween
horror we've ever faced.
And white blood cells
are attacking my clothes!
Although I must admit,
they know where to stop.
We'll have
to lighten the ship,
which means one of us
has to stay behind.
Bart... Lisa...
Fine, me.
MARGE:
Don't worry.
We'll be fine!
I'm saying good-bye
to everything I ever loved.
Ooh, a marshmallow!
Boy, when God closes a door,
He opens a window.
(giggles, gobbles)
Mom,
did you have to fly out
through all
those boogers?
Cut me some slack.
I'm a widow.
Now, there is still
a slight chance
we could rescue your husband
before he expands.
(groaning)
Uh, make that zero chance.
Frink out.
Dad, would
you like
some of my Snicker-
bar cheesecake?
Oh, I feel full
enough as it is.
I say
when we're full.
You don't wanna
piss off a man
who can kick you in
the crotch from the inside.
(groaning)
Oh, I need a mouth hole.
Um... and some
other holes, too.
Cheer up, my chubby
inner child.
I've got a feeling
everything's going to work out
fine because...
♪ I've got you... ♪
♪ Under my skin ♪
♪ I've got you ♪
♪ Deep in the heart of me ♪
♪ So deep in my heart
you're really a part of me ♪
♪ I've got you under my skin ♪
♪ Sometimes the world
looks perfect ♪
♪ Nothing to rearrange ♪
♪ Sometimes you just
get a feeling ♪
♪ Like you need some
kind of change ♪
♪ No matter what the odds
are this time ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna stand
in my way ♪
♪ This flame in my heart
and a long-lost friend ♪
♪ Gives every dark street
a light at the end ♪
♪ Standin' tall ♪
♪ On the wings of my dream ♪
♪ Rise and fall ♪
♪ On the wings of my... ♪
(Homer screaming)
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem