CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(all screaming)
(fish gulps)
LISA AND JANEY:
♪ Miss Lucy had a steamboat ♪
♪ The steamboat had a bell ♪
♪ Miss Lucy went to heaven ♪
♪ And the steamboat
went to... ♪
-(gasps)
-♪ Hello, operator ♪
-(sighs)
-♪ Get me number nine ♪
♪ And if you disconnect me,
I'll chop off your be... ♪
-(gasps)
-♪ ..hind the 'frigerator ♪
-Whoo!
-♪ There was a piece of glass ♪
♪ Miss Lucy sat upon it
and it cut her big fat... ♪
(gasps, moans)
♪ Ask me no more questions,
I'll tell you no more... ♪
Ow!
Spitballs!
I'm using your unfinished novel.
No!
You're in big trouble,
mister.
I'm bleeding.
Hmm, there's no cut
on your cheek.
Where'd the blood
come from?
Hey, I got a loose tooth.
Ew! Gross!
I bet you can't twist it.
Of course I can twist it.
I'm great.
Ow!
This is my last baby tooth.
That's the money tooth.
I heard the tooth fairy
pays triple for it.
Then let's hurry up
and rip it out of my head.
(tires squeal)
Skinner! Your bus driver
just totaled my Camry!
Can I offer you
the use of my Merkur?
Filled with your
Burger King cups
and wrappers?
No, thank you.
(Marge grunting)
Lousy drawer.
Potato masher's stuck
in the small spoon slot.
What kind of madman
would do that?
(grunts)
(gasps)
Ooh, Bart, honey,
I'm so sorry.
No problem.
No harm done.
I wouldn't say that.
Mm-hmm.
God, please give your daughter,
the Tooth Fairy,
the strength to carry my cash
and the integrity
not to dip her wand in the till.
What the...?
The Tooth Fairy's made
a donation in my name
to the United Way?!
That gossamer witch!
Maybe when
the Tooth Fairy saw
it was your last
baby tooth,
she realized you're not
a little boy anymore.
So she gave you
a grownup gift.
I'm not going to grow up!
Oh, yes, you are.
Why in the right light,
you're starting to get
your own muzzle.
I thought
it was chocolate milk.
Yeah, that's how it starts.
No!
I'm still a kid.
And what do kids love?
Kid stuff like this.
(groans)
Vroom, vroom!
(listlessly):
Vroom... vroom.
Oh...
What you realizing, jerk?
That I'm not a kid anymore.
That's harsh.
I knew I was an adult
the day the judge said,
"We're trying you as an adult."
Well, there's one thing
no one can take away--
my childlike imagination.
Sergeant Activity,
your mission is to scale
the icy walls of Mt. Bloodkill.
Must defeat Dr. Blizzard
and the Avalanchoids.
Lieutenant Adventure,
what are you doing here?
You're quite the daredevil,
Sergeant Activity.
It's high time
you protected yourself
with supplemental
disability insurance.
At my age? Can I qualify?
You'd be surprised.
If you're a non-smoker,
it can cost just
a few dollars a month.
What's happening to me?
Maybe I'm not
a kid anymore.
Goodbye Spirogram,
goodbye Sketch-N-Etch,
goodbye Ravenous
Ravenous Rhinos,
Duopoly, Parchoosey,
Humor Putty
and Sock 'Em Knock
'Em Cyborgs.
Goodbye, childhood.
♪ Dust in the wind ♪
♪ All we are
is dust in the wind ♪
Goodbye, friends.
SEA CAPTAIN:
"So Eden sank to grief,
so dawn goes down today.
Nothing gold can stay."
Yar.
Hey, Sea Captain.
Giving your toys
a Viking funeral, eh?
I really don't want
to talk about it.
If you change your mind,
I won't be far.
Thanks, but...
I've been told
I'm a good listener.
But when you're a captain,
you never know when people
are just flattering you. Yar.
He's gone.
Darn it!
I just want a friend
who isn't a work friend.
Bart, if you don't
get up now,
good luck getting a pancake.
Dad's pulled his chair
right up to the stove.
Lis, I think I'm having
a mid-life crisis.
If you're
feeling depressed,
do what I do
and write something--
a novel, a play.
Or I could write something
that's not gay.
(gasps)
Bart, someone wrote something
-cynical on your shirt.
-Mm-hmm.
-Let me wash it off.
-Leave me alone.
This expresses my rage
at the machine.
Well, I like T-shirts
with a nice joke.
Like, "Support Our Troops."
Bart's shirt
is a classic, Marge,
just like "Keep on Truckin'."
As if I would ever
want to stop truckin'.
Whoa.
I wish I had that shirt.
It's clever, funny,
and would cover my boy boobs
nicely.
♪ I'm too sexy for my shirt ♪
♪ Too sexy for my shirt ♪
♪ So sexy it hurts ♪
♪ I'm too sexy for Milan ♪
♪ Too sexy for Milan... ♪
Bart, I need
that shirt.
I'll trade you Puppy Goo Goo
for it.
She still has a lot of her
original strawberry scent.
Forget it.
My attitude
isn't for sale.
What am I saying?
Of course it is.
T-shirts!
Get your sassy T-shirts!
50% cotton, 100% awesome.
Daddy,
can I buy this one?
Let's see.
"Get bent."
Well, the only thing
that could mean is
"kneel down
and pray."
We'll take
the whole box.
Get bent, everyone.
This could get me out of a lot
of sticky situations.
I'll take a dozen.
(laughing)
Do you have a T-shirt
with Calvin peeing on Hobbes?
Sorry.
Ah. Well, what do you
got him peeing on?
(police siren)
Well, well, well.
Selling T-shirts
without a permit,
and it looks like
one of the lights
in your sneakers is out.
(grunts)
Come on, Chief.
I can't afford
to pay protection
to you and Nelson.
Mm-hmm.
Well, then, you're out
of business, boy.
Let's go, boys.
Confiscate his merchandise.
Uh, are any of those my size?
Extra-extra-extra
extra-extra...
(inhales):
...extra-extra large?
Here you go, Chief.
"Proud Nubian Princess."
Score!
(groans)
BART:
It's no fair.
I just started,
and I'm out of business.
Why don't you go legit
and sell your shirts in stores?
But I'm just a kid.
You're a kid
no longer, Bart.
You've become a man.
Hey, you're right. I am.
And as an adult,
you'll be needing
comprehensive
insurance.
I'll just leave
these brochures.
So how can I get
my shirts in stores?
I bet you could
find a distributor
at the Springfield Novelty Expo.
That's right.
It's tomorrow.
(goofy, sideshow sounds)
Oh, my God,
it's a small retailer.
He could make or break us.
MAN:
Mr. Retailer!
Over here!
Your customers
will love these
mood lollipops.
Every lick
reveals your mood.
It works.
If blue is the color
for "unimpressed."
T-shirts. Come order
my homemade T-shirts.
My mom thinks they're good!
MAN:
♪ Are y'all ready for this? ♪
(loud music playing)
(breaking, thudding)
Hey!
Hey, hey.
Krusty Show T-shirts are made
for kids by kids.
And we pass the "slavings"
on to you.
(goofy laugh)
We've got all
your favorite characters--
Itchy, Scratchy, Poochy,
Austin Powers Itchy,
Itchy Poochy,
Scratchbob Itchpants,
Confederate Itchy,
and Osama Bin Scratchy.
-Oh...
-Oh, that's great.
Oh, oh, look at that.
That sucked.
Well, at least
I've still got my health.
(brakes squealing, grunting)
(silly, instrumental version
of "La Cucaracha" plays)
Oh, my golly
graciousness.
Bad car.
Apologize
to the poor little boy.
(wah-wah horn sounds)
(laughing)
This shirt is humorlarious.
Let's see what else
you've got.
Amazing,
trailblazing,
insightful,
delightful,
hysterical,
a miracle!
The kids'll go cuckoo
for these.
(cuckoo)
(laughs)
My name's
Goose Gladwell.
Of Goose's Gags and Gifts?!
That's right.
I've got 20 stores
in 30 states,
and I want to sell your shirts
in most of them.
You really think
my shirts will sell?
"Absotivally."
Here, take my card.
Sorry.
That's my old number.
Let me give you the new one.
(laughs)
Darn. It's out of ink.
But my phone number's
on the pen.
Oh, but it's my old
phone number.
I'll call you.
I've been reading
this magazine
for years,
but I never dreamed
my son would be
on the cover.
Hmm.
("La Cucaracha" plays)
It's Goose!
-What the...?
-Huh?
Hello, Simpsons.
(all gasping):
Ooh!
You broke in!
We're big fans,
Mr. Gladwell.
Yeah.
Nothing makes
parents happier
than when
an eccentric
single man
takes an
interest
in their child.
Bart, that's your share
of the T-shirt profits so far.
ALL:
Ooh!
Look at all
that cash.
And now, it's time
for me to leave!
(circus music plays
on organ)
What a delightful sprite!
(snoring)
Smithers, there seems
to be some sort
of communiqué
on that man's blouse.
I believe it says,
"Don't wake me.
I'm working."
(muttering)
Bolshevism!
Sheer Bolshevism!
Ripe for the quashing.
(grunts, mutters)
What? Huh?
You're suspended
without pay.
Take your clacking balls
and go.
(clacking)
And on your way out,
remove all the fillings you got
under our dental plan.
You know what, Mr. Burns?
I'm never coming back.
My son's making
so much cash
in the T-shirt game,
that I don't
have to work
another day
in my life.
Assuming my health does not
deteriorate as I age.
Good riddance
to bad blubber.
Smithers, want to go
get a cup of coffee?
I just had one, sir.
What the...?
Why is everyone
so insolent today?
Well, today is Christmas, sir.
I say when it's Christmas.
ANNOUNCER:
Too much change around
the house got you down?
(musical clinking)
Help me, Romco Change Magician!
The Change Magician
will change your life
for the better!
Order today!
(gasps)
Bart, can I ask you
an important question?
How much?
$29.99.
-Oh, here's 50.
-Whoo-hoo!
That's your donut money,
too, Mister.
Oh!
Lenny, Carl,
how you doing?
Hey, Homer.
How's retirement?
It's awesome.
You know what I've gotten into?
Sleeping till noon.
Yeah.
Well, we better get going.
Some of us have to get up
for work tomorrow.
Hey, just 'cause
I'm not working
doesn't mean
I can't gripe
like you guys.
Don't you hate it
when people steal your lunch
out of the break room fridge?
Actually, that stopped
after you left, Homer.
Yeah, well,
enjoy the autumn
of your years, jerk.
Oh, I see what's going on.
You can't stand
to be around a guy
who's got total
financial independence.
Your bill, sir.
No problem.
Bart, I need $200!
Dad, the bill's only 100.
I broke some
bathroom fixtures.
(groans)
-Pathetic.
-I'm pathetic?
Because I take
money from my
ten-year-old son?
Well, let me
tell you something.
I still call
the shots around here.
Homer, use your inside voice.
I don't have an inside voice!
The wild Serengeti--
home of Africa's equivalent
to the mountain lion,
the regular lion.
These toothy Tarzan-munchers
have a rigid hierarchy
with a single alpha male
ruling the pride...
(roars)
(yawns loudly)
...until a younger,
more aggressive lion
challenges his power.
(whimpering groan)
(groans)
Oh, the couch
is like that tree.
The displaced male
has two choices:
either spend
the rest of his days
among the other
broken-down old lions...
All the good graves
are taken.
...or find inclusion
in the tribe
by caring
for vulnerable young cubs.
Hmm.
Lisa, basic cable
said I should nurture you.
Great. Will you play
Malibu Stacy with me?
Okay, you be the girl
and I'll be the car.
(humming)
I'm going
to the organic market.
(Homer vrooms)
(screeches)
(imitates siren)
Screw the market,
we're going to Mexico!
(giggles)
Whee!
HOMER:
It's El Flanderino.
-Run him down!
-(imitating engine revving)
I can't run;
I'm wearing flip flops!
(both cackling)
(both laughing)
Hey, what's that dealie?
It's my entry for the
all-school science fair.
It shows the history
of nuclear physics,
from Marie Curie's laboratory
to a scale model of
the first nuclear reactor.
Oh, you'll win
for sure.
You and science go together
like Lenny and Carl.
The science is Carl.
BOY:
Oh, Lisa!
I'd like to introduce you
to the next winner
of the science fair.
Behold! My project.
Childlike Humanoid
Urban Muchacho--
Or... CHUM!
Don't hold my hand.
It's creepy.
Hush, my pet.
Now let us gather
our rosebuds while we may.
(shivering groan)
A robot?!
Last year the winner
was a jar of owl pellets.
Oh, I don't have
a chance now.
Honey, all you
need's a little
help from your dad.
Remember, I did
used to work
at a science factory.
Well, we're supposed to do this
without parental help.
Sweetie, that's orphan talk.
(clanging and Homer grunting)
Stupid atomic pile!
How hard could it be
to build a reactor?
Korea did it, and look at
the quality of their animation.
Hmm, what to do, what to do.
Hey, maybe the Internet
has the information I need.
It certainly answered
a lot of my questions
about wang enhancement.
www.nuclear-secrets.com.
"Are you a terrorist?"
No.
"Would you like
to meet someone special
but are tired of the bar scene?"
No. I will never tire
of the bar scene.
Let's see, I can make that.
You can get that
by smashing open a golf ball.
That you can find
in any player piano.
All I need is some plutonium,
and I know just the place
to get it.
("Theme From The Pink
Panther" playing)
(chuckles)
Dad?
Bu-bu-bu-bu-bu!
Don't look.
Dad, what did you do?
Sweetie, your daddy
is going to show you
just how much he loves you.
You know that non-functioning
nuclear reactor you built?
Yes?
I juiced it up a little.
(giggling)
Dad, that could explode.
Oh, that's ridiculous.
KRUSTY:
That thing's gonna blow!
Drop this toy and run!
Mom, Dad built a device
that would be deadly
in the wrong hands,
and he's holding it.
Homer, I want you
to get that damn
irradiating whatsit
out of my home.
Oh, mmm, I never complain
about your
frilly pillows.
How many T-shirts
do you have here?
Just one.
It takes a Marine honor guard
to fold it.
It used to be a dust cover
for a Hummer.
I could go on and on.
Gravies and lentilmen,
I have an exciting announcement.
I have sold the rights
to the Bart Simpson
T-shirt line...
(crowd gasping)
to the Disney Company,
which will turn each one
into a movie.
Really?
How much money do I get?
You get nothing.
In fact,
thanks to my team
of loopy lawyers...
I never have to give you
another penny.
All you get
is a very valuable lesson.
Never trust a weirdo.
A-zoot!
Ah! I'm stuck on a nail!
Ah-ha-ha...
Ow, God, that's painful.
-(thud)
-(groaning)
I can't feel my...
(loud boing)
What's the matter, boy?
Goose Gladwell ripped me off,
and there's nothing
I can do about it.
I'm just a stupid kid.
(crying)
Son, when you grew up,
I grew down,
and now I can see
you need your dad
more than ever.
And Homer, I can see
you need me more than ever.
Get back in the garage,
old man.
But there's spiders
in the boxes.
Stay out of my boxes!
You give my son
what he deserves,
or I'll knock you on your
delightfully offbeat ass.
(chuckling):
Whoa, I must warn you, sir.
I was a Green Beret
in Vietnam.
The things I saw there
are what made me crazy!
Sir, this is a class two
plutonium fission reactor.
If I turn this dial,
the resulting blast
would destroy
the entire Tri-City area,
including that guy who sells
those Blu-Blocker sunglasses
people sometimes wear.
Damn him to hell.
You can't be serious.
Are you prepared
to take that chance?
Okay, okay, here's
all the money I've got.
Not so fast.
I also want, um...
some dribble glasses
fake boobs,
two of Bart's
T-shirts
and that rapping
toilet seat.
♪ Yo, yo, yo, keep it
on a low flow ♪
(chuckling)
I'm hanging this
over the mantel.
Thanks, Dad.
Well, I'm just glad
we're back
to me being the father
and you being the son.
Are you sure that thing
could really explode?
Oh, I doubt it.
But we'll let the seagulls
at the dump figure it out.
(Bart and Homer laughing)
BART: Yeah.
There's more than one way
to lose a tooth.
Hey, idiot, you're fat,
and your mom's naked
on the Internet.
You also smell.
Mmm... you've given me
a lot to think about.
Shh!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem