♪ Oh, you want a villain?
Let me show you how I evil ♪
♪ Oh, you think I'm difficult?
I'll show you all my devil ♪
♪ Sharpshooter, lethal
'Cause I'm a messy, feminine diesel ♪
♪ Wow ♪
♪ Paint the town blue
Riots all around you ♪
♪ Riot ♪
♪ Paint the town blue
Riots all around you ♪
♪ Crush, crush, crush
Crush you all beneath me ♪
♪ You bitches are my pups
You're droolin' for a squeaky ♪
♪ I skewer all you said
Now the battlefield is greasy ♪
♪ Dig my nails into your peach
You know, 'cause we are not amici ♪
♪ Paint the town blue
Riots all around you ♪
♪ Riot ♪
♪ Paint the town blue
Riots all around you ♪
♪ I wake up to the sounds
Of the silence that allows ♪
♪ For my mind to run around
With my ear up to the ground ♪
♪ I'm searching to behold
The stories that are told ♪
♪ When my back is to the world
That was smiling when I turned ♪
♪ Tell you you're the greatest ♪
♪ But once you turn, they hate us ♪
♪ Oh, the misery ♪
♪ Everybody wants to be my enemy ♪
♪ Oh, spare the sympathy ♪
♪ Pray it away, I swear
I'll never be a saint, no way ♪
♪ My enemy ♪
♪ Pray it away, I swear
I'll never be a saint ♪
♪ Look out for yourself ♪
Up again?
The city's not going anywhere.
I have an audience with the Masons' Guild
first thing in the morning.
Let me guess.
Complaints about the Noxians.
Hmm. They doubled
their fortification requests.
Again. To keep--
Keep us safe.
I never expected this to go on so long.
I thought...
I don't know what I thought.
Just...
it wasn't this.
You could call it off.
Withdraw from the underground.
Reestablish the Council.
All you have to do is give the order.
Not without Jinx.
Besides, a withdrawal could lead
to a worse situation than the one--
Ah. Okay, Ambessa.
She delivered us Zaun,
as she vowed.
Without her, who knows
how many Enforcers we'd have lost?
I've learned so much from her.
You're our leader.
The Enforcers, Piltover, they follow you.
I follow you.
I'll come to bed soon.
Ladies and gentlemen,
you're in the wrong place.
Scumbags and scalawags,
put your hooks and paws together
for the meanest, ugliest,
goriest spectacle of your lives.
In the gray corner,
our undefeated champion.
With claws like daggers
and teeth like sharper daggers.
The devilish,
the wretched
Stink Maw!
And in the other gray corner,
the challenger.
A rising star,
with hideous mandibles
and a face
that would make a brood mother squirm.
The creepy,
the dastardly
Scuttle Butt!
Two will enter.
And after that, who knows?
Handlers, release your beasts.
No, no. What are you doing?
Show some effort.
Congratulations on your victory.
Well, you're past your prime, champ.
Only thing to do is--
Hmm. A rematch?
Return of the titans.
Vengeance. Redemption.
The inexplicable release of bodily gases.
All right, all right.
I still think it's a dumb idea.
But I guess you won, and a deal's a deal.
I guess.
Ta-da!
You like it?
You're lucky.
I didn't get to do much of this
with my older sis.
She was more into...
hitting things.
I had a different name back then,
you know.
Powder.
Stupid, right?
I thought I was rid of her
for good, but, uh...
you kind of remind me of her.
Pew.
Did Sevika put you up to this?
That's a past life, kid.
And it was about as sweet
as last year's milk.
Jinx is dead.
Hmm.
How, in a city teeming
with brilliant inventors,
have we managed to unearth
such unrelenting incompetence?
This is their doing.
We can't be certain the Black--
Keep their name out of your mouth.
We can't be certain the Order
was also behind the disappearance
of Jayce and Heimerdinger.
Who else?
The moment we seize control
of this backwater,
everyone with an inkling
of talent vanishes.
It's no coincidence.
Our instincts were right.
They fear Hextech.
But we were too slow.
How could I not secure the scientists?
They have my daughter, Rictus.
Our moment will come.
But you must be prepared.
To expedite processing,
have any and all bags open
and ready for examination.
Officers ask for your cooperation
and compliance
as we make every attempt to ensure
the safety and security of Piltover.
Next. Move along.
To expedite processing...
You have Jinx to thank for this.
She is not your friend.
She is not your champion.
She hides while you suffer.
And yet you refuse to hand her over.
...the safety of all citizens...
♪ I just wanna blow shit up ♪
♪ Let's blow shit up ♪
♪ I wanna blow shit up... ♪
Let's go.
♪ Set this place on fire ♪
Jinx.
You're right.
It's hers.
I'd recognize it anywhere.
That's where the similarities end.
No body count. No theatrics.
You think it's a copycat?
I think we've made them desperate
for something to believe in.
This doesn't have to change what we talked
about this morning. You can still--
Officer Nolen.
Quite the familiar face these days.
General.
I'd like a word with Commander Kiramman.
In private.
I suppose I don't need to advise you
on the hazards
of professional entanglements.
Nor is that the advice
you rushed here to provide.
It's beyond question
that the news of Jinx's return
will ignite Zaunite resistance.
But the blade cuts both ways.
There's a trail.
We have her scent.
I'd expected this development
would encourage you.
Was it for my encouragement that
your man Rictus was instigating violence?
You don't trust me.
"The blade cuts both ways."
Fearless child.
You never shy.
You have a recommendation?
If it wasn't Jinx at the checkpoint,
one of them knows where she is.
Arrests require cause.
What greater cause is there
than returning peace to this city?
Why is peace
always the justification for violence?
We've lost so many.
The anger, the sorrow...
It's tiring.
Gods, I know it's tiring.
But you will never rest
knowing that she's out there.
Or maybe I underestimated you.
Maybe you have the strength I do not.
To forgive
and trust in tomorrow.
The decision is yours, commander.
I hosted the most lavish galas
in the city.
It was a measure of status
to be on my guest list.
Toast of the town.
Now people avert their gaze
when I roll by.
My gaze isn't averted.
Oh, spare me.
I wouldn't have hired you
if you weren't versed in the art
of indulging your clients' egos.
Plus you're one of the few councilors
left from the old batch, right?
Never learned anything
about the younger Medarda, did they?
Even when she's not here,
she's all anyone talks about.
I get it.
She's the last heir of the great Medardas.
But the writing's on the wall.
When you're missing this long,
you're not coming back.
- Same time next week?
- Tomorrow.
The effects have been diminishing.
Huh.
I keep hearing about this healer
down in the fissures,
way out on the fringes.
They say he makes miracles happen.
I saw one.
Like nothing I'd ever seen before.
Can't hurt to look, can it?
You could have warned me.
Fat chance. About what?
Your stunt at the checkpoint.
No idea what you're babbling about.
That wasn't you?
Hmm.
Well, however it happened,
the whole undercity's buzzing,
saying you're back.
- So I'm thinking--
- Not your strong suit.
Would make a world of difference
if you showed up.
You're a symbol.
Ha. You want a symbol?
Silco spent his whole life
trying to rally the undercity together.
Stupid joke that it is,
you have the chance to pull it off.
I told you, I'm not interested.
Do you know how much
he sacrificed to protect you?
He believed in your potential.
Well, then he shouldn't have died!
We're having a rally tonight.
Vander's statue.
Firelights, your fans...
Anyone I can bring to the table.
Stick your head in the dirt if you want,
but this fantasy
you've been living out here,
it's not gonna last forever.
Don't trip on the way out.
I don't know how you do it, kid.
I gotta go bother someone.
Still giving me the silent treatment, huh?
Between you and Isha,
I'm losing my snappy comebacks.
Me, a hero.
How screwed up is this place?
I know Sevika's right,
and I probably owe it to you,
on account of the murdering and all.
But I got something going now.
A friend.
And I don't want to mess it up.
Maybe that's what I was like for you.
If you care so much about me
playing your stupid revolution game,
speak up now, or I guess...
I guess you...
You're really gone.
And there's no reason
to stay here anymore.
Statue...
Vander's statue...
It's no secret we got history.
Blood spilt on all sides.
But we grew up on the same streets.
Ate the same scraps.
Like it or not,
we're in this mess together.
Enforcers raiding our homes.
Noxians down our throats.
Innocents getting carted off
to Stillwater.
We gotta choose right now
whether we're gonna throw in the towel
or make a stand together.
Not as Firelights
or Jinxers
or washed-up goons.
- As Zaunites.
- We wanna see Jinx!
Where is Jinx?
Where is she?
We wanna see Jinx!
Yeah, where is she?
Yeah, where's Jinx?
You're all under arrest.
- Drop the blade.
- Drop it.
Drop the blade.
I'm back.
Time to find out
who's the new pebbleweight--
Hmm? Isha?
Okay, I get it.
We're playing that game, are we?
Isha?
They got her.
What?
She came to the rally.
Topside raided the place.
Took everyone.
You know what you are.
- Damn it, Powder!
- Shut up. Shut up.
Shut up. Shut up.
Stop calling me that.
Her name is Jinx.
She's my sister.
- Jinx.
- You have to be someone else.
Jinx.
Chin up, little one.
I'll tell you a secret.
We won't be staying long.
Don't suppose you can swim, huh, Lefty?
Well, only leaves the fun option.
I'm gonna hate this, aren't I?
Ha! It's me.
Your vile villainess.
The author of your nightmares.
The, uh, dread of your--
Who are you?
Mm, Jinx?
Yeah, never heard that before.
You're not gonna haul me in?
Claim the prize? Be the big hero?
You expect me to believe Jinx,
the master criminal,
wears pants like that?
What's wrong with my pants?
You look like
a half-eaten circus tent.
Ugh! I am Jinx.
"Half-eaten."
Can we focus?
Oh... Oh, oh, oh...
Let's go.
Whoo! Big mama.
How'd you take her in?
I gave her a choice between this
and a swim in the harbor.
Cell Block C. Carry on, officer.
Yes, sir.
Move it.
Come on, man. I have a kid.
You can't keep us in here.
Here I am,
your big fat hero.
You're late for
Stink Maw's great comeuppance.
What the hell was that?
Move it.
Stand down.
Get her out.
You really are a--
Big fat hero.
You got me, hairball.
But just remember...
you're no Stink Maw.
Smile.
Powder?