Drink the moment, Mel Medarda.
There is no time like your first.
I'm one of you?
A mage?
We each have
our own expressions.
Yours is quite rare.
An empath.
Attuned to the ethereal.
Able to sense others' inner selves
and bend their magic.
A conduit and a mirror.
What does that make you?
Even now you hide your true face
behind illusions.
Truth is
the greatest illusion of them all.
I think beneath that mask you're scared.
I can see through your tricks.
That makes me a threat.
For the gifted,
arrogance is the ultimate threat.
Your power has merit.
But should one want you dead,
a simple blade would do nicely.
Where is my brother?
Regrettably, his fate wasn't
among your mother's lies.
You killed him.
I gave Ambessa every opportunity
to atone for her transgressions.
She chose pride over progeny.
But you need not bear her crimes.
The test.
This whole charade.
You want to recruit me.
Your talents developed quickly.
It's no coincidence.
The Arcane is waking up.
What has my mother done?
A calamity is approaching,
rivaling even the ancient Rune Wars.
Ambessa sits at the helm,
blinded by her thirst for legacy.
Our efforts to divert her course
have foundered.
We can't afford another failure.
This is what you see in me?
A silver bullet?
I see salvation of your city,
countless others beyond.
She's my mother.
For all her faults,
she has always done
what she thought was best for the family.
Your brother thought so too,
until he uncovered her secret.
Your birth,
the entire course of your life,
was no accident.
She hid you because you are that
which she covets most:
a weapon.
Today you've been born into a new family,
from which you'll find
there is sadly no return.
Those untouched by the Arcane fear us.
What is this?
A welcome to your future.
The world is a perilous place
for a solitary mage...
sister.
I regret
that I couldn't save him.
His injuries were too severe.
We do not lament
a warrior's death.
We avenge it.
What of their Herald?
The blood should sustain Viktor
for a short while.
Beyond that, it is up to his own will.
You promised a cure to death.
An outcome dependent on Viktor's survival.
Doctor.
Your ingenuity deserves praise.
Viktor.
I am...
grateful.
The world I now see is more...
lucid than ever.
You can inhabit your followers?
We are one.
This is the Glorious Evolution.
Or it could have been.
I sense my twilight approaching.
An anomaly festers beneath the Hexgates.
I believe it has the capacity
to complete the doctor's transformation.
This will allow you to evolve others?
In theory.
But Jayce's attack has done its work.
I do not have the strength to overcome
the defense he will raise against me.
I will deliver you to this anomaly,
if you agree
to empower every soldier I bring you.
I will evolve all those willing.
Vi?
Come on.
We need to get out of here.
No!
Isha!
Shh. Easy there.
Took all the three docs to patch you up.
Loris?
Wasn't sure you'd pull through.
Thank that thick noggin of yours.
Where are the others?
Cait?
Jinx?
Jinx.
Caitlyn wanted to be here
to tell you herself.
Loris.
Spit it out.
Maybe we can negotiate.
Not with Ambessa.
I saw it in her eyes.
She will burn Piltover
to the ground for my betrayal.
You can't blame yourself.
I don't need consolation.
I need a plan.
Arrested?
I can handle this, Maddie.
Check on my father?
- Vi.
- She saved your life.
If you will calm down for one...
Knowing you'd never
have done the same for her.
We'll never know, will we?
You didn't let me in
on that part of your plan.
Clearly the right call,
since you still can't trust her enough
not to shove her in a box.
Trust?
You believe I'm so daft
I can't recognize a contingency?
She wasn't there for my benefit.
You didn't trust me to follow through.
Can you blame me?
How long were you sidled up
with that shifty, self-serving war pig?
She oinked poison in your ear.
You just ate it.
I know.
The only thing Jinx cared about
was getting you to safety.
Then she just surrendered.
I didn't even have time to think
before they hauled her off.
She's being held in the bunker
while I decide what to do.
I was waiting for you to recover.
Cait, she's changed.
We can't erase our mistakes.
None of us.
Who decides who gets a second chance?
If you're here to kill me,
make sure to finish the job.
Vi thinks you've changed.
She can't accept
what you and I know.
There are no happy endings.
Is that all you have to say for yourself?
There won't be a trial.
I'm giving you this one chance
to account for your actions,
all the pain you've caused.
No amount of good deeds
can undo our crimes.
Do what you came here to do.
Hating you...
I've hated myself.
I just don't have the energy
for it any longer.
I didn't know your mom was there.
It probably wouldn't have made
a difference, but...
I didn't know.
Jayce?
What happened to you?
Doesn't matter.
Something happened to me too.
You're the reason
we didn't die in the attack.
Apparently so.
How long have you known?
It started then.
Feelings I couldn't explain.
But this...
I still don't fully understand.
Why just me? Why not save all of them?
It wasn't a decision.
One moment you're addressing the Council,
the next we're standing in rubble.
I didn't have any greater awareness.
How can I know you aren't lying to me?
Why would you think I am?
Because you used me,
and Viktor, for Hextech.
You called us "investments."
Two brilliant young inventors who shared
a penchant for impossible surprises.
Carrying magic from myth to machine.
Rallying the hope and hearts of a nation.
You were a wise investment.
Allow us a moment of civility, Jayce.
We must talk.
Viktor.
How did you get in here?
You once benefitted
from my knowledge of this place.
That was a long time ago.
Had you given me the chance,
I would have shown you
the merits of my work.
Our work.
No, this is your obsession.
Everything you've done
to these people, you did alone.
Perhaps.
But I'm alone no longer.
I now speak with all their voices.
Say what you came here to say.
Somehow I think you already understand
what must transpire
to complete my mission.
I would prefer to do so in peace.
The Noxian has other intentions.
Mother?
The Arcane stirs within you.
Viktor, for all our sakes,
stay away from the Hexgates.
Your mind has become rigid, Jayce.
Fear clouds your judgment.
This chain of events started with you.
In my confusion,
I was unable to reconcile this.
But I now understand.
The Glorious Evolution is destined.
Let us instead do this once again
as partners.
My partner died in this room.
It was my sincere desire to avoid this.
Doctor.
You may begin the process.
Go away.
You're too late.
Oh, it's a hell of a place.
It says something about the late Marcus
that he found imprisoning your sister
to be a greater mercy than killing her.
Killing isn't mercy.
A spark of rebellion
still burns inside that husk, I see.
No.
Killing is a cycle.
One that started
long before Vander and me.
And it will continue
long after the two of you.
I'm done running in circles.
We build our own prisons.
Bars forged of oaths, codes, commitments.
Walls of self-doubt
and accepted limitation.
We inhabit these cells, these identities,
and call them "us."
I thought I could break free
by eliminating those I deemed my jailors.
But...
Jinx...
I think the cycle only ends
when you find the will to walk away.
Jinx?
What are you doing?
I swiped these from the guard station.
If you come, help, use all that
explosive potential of yours for good,
maybe we could rewrite your story,
like you did with Zaun.
What do you think?
Sure, Vi.
You're never gonna give up
on me, are you?
Hey!
You don't have to worry about me anymore.
You don't need to feel guilty
about being happy.
You deserve to be with her.
Wait.
There's no good version of me.
What are you gonna do?
Break the cycle.
Jinx!
I'm sorry.
I've been an idiot.
And an ass.
You're hurting too.
For as long as I can recall,
I have chased the archetype of a Medarda.
I believed it my calling
to merit the blood in my veins.
It was all a lie.
This blood is alien to me.
Yet it has dictated the course
of my entire life.
I'm no more than a passenger.
A life I spent in self-pity.
Now it's gone.
I can never return to it.
I've been confused about a lot lately.
But there's one thing I know in my bones.
There is no force in this world
that can control you.
You will never be a passenger.
Quiet.
Forgive me.
But we don't have much time.
A storm is coming,
the likes of which Piltover,
perhaps Runeterra itself, has never faced.
This creature infiltrated
the very room you're standing in.
And we barely survived.
Hundreds more are on the way.
The Noxian general is leading them.
This isn't a fight for ideals
or territory.
It's a fight for humanity itself.
I'm asking...
No, begging you, every one of you,
Topside and bottom,
to aid us in this coming war.
And it will be a war.
Now, this isn't a fair request,
but it is our only hope.
The forces against us are too great.
We need every hand we can get.
Bring them down!
We're abandoning the city's outskirts
to stage our defense at the Hexgates.
The final bastion of our salvation.
If you choose to flee, don't stop running.
But I'm choosing to fight.
And I pray that you will join me.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Just a moment.
Here, ma'am.
Had a feeling I might find you here.
I really believed she'd help.
Say it.
You told me so.
I was an idiot to trust her.
I went behind your back.
I choose wrong every time.
And because of it, I've lost everyone.
You really think I needed
all the guards at the Hexgates?
Sorry to say,
you've grown a bit predictable.
Uh, listen, while you were gone,
I saw someone...
Cait.
I don't fucking care.
Take watch of the Herald.
You're alive.
I know about the Black Rose.
You know a facade.
They are nothing but lies.
You taught me
the best lies come wrapped in truth.
What really happened to Kino?
Your brother was struck with curiosity.
He got caught in their web
and, with every action,
grew more deeply entangled.
So you let him die?
I carried him in my belly,
nursed him from my bosom.
He was all the sweetness in my heart.
For that, they took him,
carved into me a wound
that will never close.
I pray you never suffer the agony
of being forced
to forsake one child to save another.
You should have come to me.
You'd have made
the impossible intolerable.
I did what you could not.
For you.
For the family.
Piltover has nothing to do with your feud.
Board your boats, leave our shores.
I will join you.
We can avenge Kino together.
This is more
than vengeance, child.
These mages dangle over our heads a sword
that impales us should we rise too high.
Their very nature violates
the most core of Noxian principles,
that every one of us is equal
on the battlefield.
That through cunning,
sweat,
and steel...
we shape our destinies.
The fact you've come
to parley for your friends' lives prove
you still lack the wrath necessary
to defeat an enemy like the Rose.
I've found another way.
Imagine, child,
an army that need never fear death.
What have you done, Mother?
Doctor.
You may begin the process.
Very well.
I guess this is goodbye.
Thank you very much for your company
in my solitude, Ms. Young.
I will miss our talks.
No.
You won't.