♪ I've held on for as long as I can ♪
♪ For the ones that I had to defend ♪
♪ I've been strong every day of my life ♪
♪ If she wants
Death could take me this time ♪
♪ This world is a wasteland
Where nothing can grow ♪
♪ I used to have strength
But I ran out of hope ♪
♪ I know it's my fault
That I'm here all alone ♪
♪ This world is a wasteland ♪
♪ Please let me go ♪
♪ Go, go, go ♪
♪ If I could just lay my head down
And rest ♪
♪ If there was nothing to fight
Or protect ♪
♪ Maybe then I could finally be free ♪
♪ Maybe death is like falling asleep ♪
♪ This world is a wasteland
Where nothing can grow-- ♪
Wait!
I just wanna talk to you.
Get out of here, Ekko.
I just...
I just wanna talk to you, Pow--
Jinx.
- You're too late, Ekko.
- Wait!
Always a dance with you.
I think I'm just gonna sit here a minute.
You know, catch my breath.
See if I can talk an old friend
out of blowing us up.
- I'm tired of talking.
- No!
No! No! No...
You know, I learned from someone...
very special...
that no matter what happened in the past,
it's never too late
to build something new.
Someone worth building it for.
♪ ...go, go ♪
♪ Go, go, go ♪
♪ Please let me go ♪
♪ I wake up to the sounds
Of the silence that allows ♪
♪ For my mind to run around
With my ear up to the ground ♪
♪ I'm searching to behold
The stories that are told ♪
♪ When my back is to the world
That was smiling when I turned ♪
♪ Tell you you're the greatest ♪
♪ But once you turn, they hate us ♪
♪ Oh, the misery ♪
♪ Everybody wants to be my enemy ♪
♪ Oh, spare the sympathy ♪
♪ Pray it away, I swear
I'll never be a saint, no way ♪
♪ My enemy ♪
♪ Pray it away, I swear
I'll never be a saint ♪
♪ Look out for yourself ♪
I need you and the Enforcers
to buy me as much time as you can
so I can shut down the Hexgates.
It's our only chance.
Viktor's at the center
of all this, isn't he?
We're meant to lose this fight.
If he reaches the Hexgates...
Then we'd best stop him.
Move, move!
Reinforce the forward artillery.
We can't let them break through.
- Go.
- Let's go.
- Hold it.
- Go.
Reload.
- Give her some air.
- You're okay.
Down!
- Back!
- Come on.
Let's go.
Around the gate!
Bold, little one.
- Move your units and wait there.
- Stay.
Come on!
Let's go, let's go.
I warned you of the hazards
of professional entanglement.
Desperation is the doorway
to oblivion, child.
Let's get this over with.
I did appreciate your warmth.
If you care for me at all,
spare their lives.
There is nothing to gain
from this senseless bloodshed.
Still a fox.
Soldier.
Get in line.
♪ You're not alone ♪
♪ Look at my shadow
Right behind you like a ghost ♪
♪ If we should die
Our legend is our rare flow ♪
♪ Taking those shots
Make the big throws, bespoke ♪
♪ Tell them straight, coz
Turn them all to stone ♪
Fire!
Let's run.
Hmm.
Where is Viktor?
Despite the circumstances, Jayce...
I am... pleased to see you.
There must be some part
of you still in there.
I am more than I ever was.
What other choice do we have?
Mother, look at the price
of your ambition.
You've sacrificed everything.
Rictus.
Kino.
This city I built for our family.
If it was for us,
you wouldn't have fought me.
You are no Medarda.
You remember your--
Shut up and fight.
Vi!
It is the answer
you and I pursued all our lives.
An end to cruelty, injustice.
All of us our own authors
to an unbroken saga of progress.
To the benefit of all.
People deserve to choose their own fates.
Choice is false.
It is how we clothe and forgive
the baser instincts
that spur us to division.
Death, war, prejudice.
Energy spent only to consume itself.
But we can be of one mind.
United.
You fought well, child.
Now!
A wolf has no mercy.
Your daughter is wiser
than you credit.
I salute you, Ambessa.
For one without the gift,
you were quite a thorn.
What are you doing, sister?
I see your face, deceiver.
Sly girl.
You are the wolf.
Looks like you shouldn't have come back.
Still don't get it, huh, sis?
I'm always with you.
Even when we're worlds apart.
Stop this insanity, Viktor.
That is precisely my intention.
Your eyes won't lie...
when your mind...
is open, Jayce.
Vander.
Dad?
Do you see?
The sublime intersection
of order and chaos.
This is what you see?
This conflict.
This senseless waste.
I know their minds, Jayce.
They want better lives,
but emotion clashes with reason.
Humanity's self-corrupting contradiction.
You've always wanted to cure
what you thought were weaknesses.
Your leg.
Your disease.
But you were never broken, Viktor.
There is beauty in imperfections.
They made you who you are.
An inseparable piece of everything...
I admired about you.
That device can't be.
I thought I wanted us
to give magic to the world.
Now...
all I want...
is my partner back.
Why do you persist?
After everything I've done?
Because I promised you.
Why did you ever give me this?
Why?
I thought I could bring an end
to the world's suffering.
But when every equation was solved...
all that remained...
were fields of dreamless solitude.
There is no prize to perfection.
Only an end to pursuit.
In all timelines,
in all possibilities...
only you...
can show me this.
You must go, Jayce.
We finish this together.
Vi!
Vi, hurry, you can make the other ledge.
What are you...?
Vi.
Vi?
You can't save him.
Vi!
Always with you, sis.
♪ If I could just lay my head down
And rest ♪
♪ If there was nothing to fight
Or protect ♪
♪ Maybe then I could finally be free ♪
♪ Maybe death is like falling asleep ♪
♪ This world is a wasteland
Where nothing can grow ♪
♪ I used to have strength
But I ran out of hope ♪
♪ I know it's my fault
That I'm here all alone ♪
♪ This world is a wasteland ♪
♪ Please let me go ♪
♪ Go, go, go ♪
You may read
about the war in Piltover.
But history is made palatably abstract.
For its truth...
the agony of every sacrifice...
the exaltation of every triumph...
is more than one should bear.
We...
whose decisions led us here,
will carry them forever.
Our only consolation that with every loss,
we found some good,
some light,
worth gaining,
worth fighting for.
And though we are doomed
to revisit the error of our ways...
spark ever more conflicts...
our story isn't over.
Is that...
singing?
It's just a tune my mother used to hum.
Are you still in this fight, Violet?
I am the dirt under your nails, cupcake.
Nothing's gonna clean me out.