Well, it's all going to shit.
Chembarons warring
for control of the Lanes.
Wannabe street thugs
squabbling over scraps.
Just like when Vander shoved off.
Except this time...
you aren't here
to put it all back together, because...
Because someone put
all those holes in you.
Vi used to say I could fix anything.
Before I broke everything.
She used to say a lot.
Her and you.
Always bossing me around.
Now it's so quiet.
What am I supposed to do with that?
Have you had enough?
♪ I wake up to the sounds
Of the silence that allows ♪
♪ For my mind to run around
With my ear up to the ground ♪
♪ I'm searching to behold
The stories that are told ♪
♪ When my back is to the world
That was smiling when I turned ♪
♪ Tell you you're the greatest ♪
♪ But once you turn, they hate us ♪
♪ Oh, the misery ♪
♪ Everybody wants to be my enemy ♪
♪ Oh, spare the sympathy ♪
♪ Pray it away, I swear
I'll never be a saint, no way ♪
♪ My enemy ♪
♪ Pray it away, I swear
I'll never be a saint ♪
♪ Look out for yourself ♪
♪ Lonely rose on your grave ♪
♪ You poor sucker ♪
♪ One by one
All these bloodhounds keep comin' ♪
♪ Sleep in the casket you made ♪
♪ You're gone, sucker ♪
♪ Too bad if you thought I let you go ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ Get the fuck out of my head ♪
♪ So long, sucker ♪
♪ I don't wanna see you
I hate this life, whoa ♪
♪ Get your fingers out of my head ♪
♪ You're gone, sucker ♪
♪ Good luck killing me
'Cause I'm already ♪
♪ Already dead inside ♪
♪ Dirty little animals ♪
♪ You cannibals
Eat your supper ♪
♪ One by one
All these vultures keep comin' ♪
♪ Pretty little animal
Come down here ♪
♪ You're gone, sucker ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na ♪
♪ Na-na-na, na-na-na ♪
♪ Whoa, get back out of my head ♪
♪ So long, sucker ♪
♪ I don't wanna see you
I hate this life, whoa... ♪
You feel it?
That...
...buzzing behind your eyes?
Because you know, in a moment,
it could all... poow!
Hmm.
Best feeling in the world, kid.
Yep, that's me.
You ever need to curse a sibling
or a family or a society...
my card.
♪ Good luck killin' me
'Cause I'm already ♪
♪ Already dead inside ♪
Well, you know, far be it from me,
but, uh, you hired me to run the numbers.
And ever since we've gone up
against the other chembarons,
the numbers are in the, uh...
Shitter?
Not exactly the term I...
Ever wonder why fat brains like you
always wind up working for grunts like me?
No, uh, never.
You only use half your head.
Plotting moves.
Calculating odds.
Know how Silco took hold of the Lanes?
With his bare teeth.
It just, you know, seems, uh, hasty.
Last count, Margot had
at least ten hitters guarding the stash.
Margot and Chross can buck
all they want, but in the end,
I'll be the one smiling.
Until I'm in Silco's chair,
your only job is
to make the numbers work, hmm?
The Grey.
All the way up here?
What do you know? Cleared the place out.
Might have made our jobs a lot easier.
No, no, no. We can't.
It's factory smog trapped underground.
No more, no less.
Boss.
You-- You go on ahead.
Report back.
Me?
I know you're all fantasizing
about sawing each other's heads off.
So I'm gonna get right to it.
These turf wars have to stop.
These two have been the aggressors.
I've only defended my interests.
Playing coy doesn't suit you, love.
You started this dance
when you raided the Rapturewalk.
What could I want
with your boulevard of filth?
Topside is the real enemy.
Us killing each other
is playing right into their hands.
Our best shot is
to put aside these petty squabbles
and join forces.
Ally with these two?
I rather favor my chances with Topside.
Even together,
they outnumber us four to one.
That's before all the recent casualties.
Might matter up there,
but they don't know the first thing
about fighting in the fissures.
Hmm.
Is he dead?
Why is he so quiet?
She's right.
We don't get Topside off our backs,
we don't last.
But I got a different solution.
We give them Jinx.
It's all they really want.
We don't hand over our people.
"We"? You don't do much
of anything anymore, do you, magpie?
Bird without a wing's
just a funny-looking rat.
Struck a nerve, did I?
Okay, I'll make you a deal.
You help me put a bow on Baby Blue
for our friends upstairs,
I'll cut you a brand-new puncher,
top of the line, all the fixings.
Think on it.
But I promise,
it's the last offer you're gonna get.
I can't believe you're dead
and I'm still mopping up your messes.
Jeez, lady, you crazy?
Talking to dead people.
You here to finish me off?
Haven't I done you enough favors?
Same time every day.
Big baby couldn't do it himself.
- Couldn't do much himself.
- Mm.
About now, he'd have me all over the Lanes
running his collections.
Building his weapons.
Making his deals.
Exploding his enemies.
He dips out,
the whole world flips over.
All his plans.
Everything we built.
The hell we supposed to do now?
Watch it all burn.
What'd I tell you?
Viktor.
Viktor!
Viktor...
Viktor.
Jayce?
Viktor?
My God.
What...
am I?
You're...
You're alive.
You're-- You're alive.
Oh! Oh, uh...
You must be cold.
Cold.
No, I don't think so.
I sense a charge.
A potential.
A recursive impulse.
Unpleasant, but...
"cold" isn't its name.
The Hexcore.
Viktor, it saved you.
Somehow it-- It adapted to your injuries,
changing and evolving.
It was as if it was connected to you.
I did my best using the notes
from your leg. Recorded everything.
- There are still so many questions, but--
- I was supposed to die.
You promised to destroy the Hexcore.
No.
Don't you see?
Heimerdinger was wrong.
We were wrong. It's not as bad as we--
It killed Sky, Jayce.
What?
No.
She had such dreams.
As did we once.
I'm going to resign from the Council.
I understand now.
My place was always here
in the lab with you.
We'll make this right. Together.
I must say goodbye
to this place now.
To you.
Goodbye?
Viktor, you're my partner.
Our paths diverged long ago.
It was affection that held us together.
You think it's so easy?
To turn your back while your city
looks to you for salvation?
To cling to principles while
your best friend bleeds out in your arms?
I never asked for this.
Where are you going?
Goodbye, Jayce.
There's so many of them.
It's all the fighting.
We're gonna have capacity issues soon.
Then there's the security risk.
We're not turning people away.
All these years,
we finally get rid of Silco,
just so a new one can take his place.
Now watch this.
Oh, this is quite troubling.
That tree means so much.
It's our food. Fresh air.
We built our whole identity around it.
Every time it seems
like we might catch a break...
Ah, now, it's not lost yet, lad.
If there is a means of preservation,
by golly, we'll find it.
I have seen something
of this nature before.
Oh.
Ch-ch-ch.
Hmm.
Don't you essentially own this place?
Shh.
Come on.
The brambleback
has left the jungle.
Uh, you do realize code phrases don't work
when you make them up on the spot?
Shh.
Professor?
Yes, of course.
- What the devil's gotten into you?
- I thought...
Why are you breaking into my lab?
And who's he?
This is my new pupil, Ekko.
Ekko, my former pupil Jayce.
- Hmm.
I apologize for the intrusion.
We were attempting to sneak in.
Oh, pishposh. Like you've never done it.
Were you sleeping here?
You drink tea, Ekko?
Ah.
You're right.
It matches the corruption we saw
on the plants we tested with the Hexcore,
but where did you say you found this?
Deep in the underground.
Ekko's home is a marvelous place.
Truly a wonder.
- You should see what--
- Hey.
Uh, right, uh, when I said "home,"
I was, of course,
referring to his cognitive center.
- Not a physical location hidden in the...
- Heimer, what are you doing?
Did any of the plants survive?
They weren't what we were trying to save.
But this pattern.
How could it be there and here?
Oh, no.
Where's Viktor?
It's okay.
Viktor.
Hmm.
It's all clear.
Sorry, commander.
Baby Blue.
Right through their fingers.
You must be part eel.
Just means I can up my finder's fee.
There's always a deal to be struck.
Ah, ah, ah. They want you alive.
But don't think
I won't skewer out those peepers.
Drawback of you long-range types.
Me? I'm the kind of guy
who likes to get in close.
Never thought I'd catch you blubbering.
Wonder if Silco even saw that.
Twice.
When he met me
and when I killed him.
You?
It's always me.
Whether I'm pulling the pin or not,
everyone who gets close to me dies.
Wanna know the real kicker?
You're the kind of guy
who likes to get in close.
♪ Whoo, yeah ♪
♪ Badness, yeah ♪
♪ Ah! ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
♪ This is copin'
And you're showing up ♪
♪ Bad beef from the East to Europe
And just fold it up ♪
♪ Try to show me up
'Cause they're loving the way I bus... ♪
♪ If we walkin', ain't no stoppin'
'Cause police don't give a fuck ♪
♪ Who you with, what your color
Your papa, your mother, son ♪
♪ Who you diss for 1 million... ♪
♪ This the gun, tell these bitches
We never run ♪
♪ We're low, we're low ♪
♪ Yeah, we come to kill her ♪
♪ We're low, we're low, we're low ♪
♪ Yeah, we come to kill her... ♪
Poow.
Hmm?
♪ I'm never gonna let you in ♪
♪ Gonna break it down, burn the ground
I'm a fire starter ♪
♪ You're the bullet and I'm the gun
Bad bitches never run ♪
♪ Never run, run, run ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
♪ This the gun, tell these bitches
We never run ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
♪ Shoot faster ♪
♪ Just a little bit of-- ♪
Huh?
♪ Do you ever wanna catch me? ♪
♪ So can you say a little louder ♪
♪ I'm really getting bored ♪
♪ Do you ever wanna catch me? ♪
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
There's a deal to be struck here.
You forget, Smeech?
You already made your last offer.
♪ This the gun, tell these bitches
We never run ♪
Tell me,
who's a funny-looking rat now?
Fancy meeting you here.
Moron never could keep
his damn mouth shut.
You could've just let me eat it.
Haven't I done you enough favors?
I didn't ask you for this.
It was something I could fix.
You got that look in your eye again.
What are you planning?
To finish what's left of my family.
Oh, God.
Viktor.
Careful not to scrape up the gear.
Won't sell as well.
Nothing personal, friend.
We just got needs we can't ignore.
So much senseless pain.
What are you doing?
You need not suffer anymore.
But...