Well, folks there he is,
the butterflyweight champion
of the Piltover Boxing League,
Gustove "The Scowler" Jowler!
Looking good, sis.
Wait, just--
I don't wanna hear another word
out of your mouth.
It's Vander.
I'm not falling
for another one of your tricks.
He's...
alive.
We both know that's bullshit.
He needs our help.
I can prove it.
Months of peacekeeping occupation.
Countless operations.
Oceans of sweat and tears.
I'd begun to think we might finally see
an end to Zaun's perverse abominations.
How foolish was I?
The beast came for you.
It was summoned by you.
In my experience,
only guilty men
answer accusations with silence.
In my experience,
no one in power is innocent.
There are cells
buried deep within this prison
so devoid of light
and fresh air
and all basic human considerations
that up till now,
I have forbidden their use.
If you do not want to waste away
the remainder of your days
in one of these, you have one recourse.
Tell us everything we need to know
to hunt down this beast.
Your youth betrays you.
Patience is a product of age.
Both of which I possess in abundance.
This is your final chance.
Tell me what you were planning.
How was Jinx involved?
You will rot in here.
Elora?
Black Rose.
Hope you find these quarters
to your liking.
They still haven't replied
to my requests for a transfer.
Who's there?
Not sure I know anymore.
Our hosts have a way
of scrambling your omelet.
They killed my friend.
Elora was there.
And then...
Elora!
Ah. The stewards of the old world
are always keen
to give you a glimpse of their might.
What is this place?
Near as I can tell,
an Oculorum.
According to legend,
the ancients built specialized chambers
to seal away false prophets.
But if you ask me,
they're just the fancy pits
peacock princes like
to toss their friends into.
Peacock princes?
Sorry, just an old family joke.
You know, the kind of rulers
with an artistic flair.
Step into the light.
Kino?
It's me, brother.
Mel.
You've grown up.
I'd hoped they'd never come for you.
This is where I lost him.
Cool, huh?
Not even toxic.
Pretty sure.
Why would Vander be all the way down here?
Beats me.
Ask him yourself.
When will you admit
that this is just one of your fantasies?
Or do you not want the kid
to know how delusional you are?
She wasn't always like this.
She actually used to be pretty cool,
before I kicked her butt.
See what I mean?
Delusional.
Wish I was just seeing things
when you decided
to throw in with the Piltie goons
who murdered Mom and Dad.
At least they never had to see
the psycho their daughter turned into.
Which one?
Wake up, sis.
I'm a hero.
I busted half of Zaun out of Stillwater
while you were passed out
in the bottom of a mug.
Now can it and keep walking,
before I kick your ass again.
You wouldn't last one second
without all your ugly gadgets
and chickenshit tricks.
Ha! What about those
overdesigned bitch-mittens
you didn't even build yourself?
You think I need these to--?
There. One second.
Last chance to surrender.
Go right ahead, fat hands.
Hey, kid.
Still got all your insides?
Mm.
But don't ditch us.
Why'd you come get me?
You don't actually need my help.
You haven't for a long time.
Last time Vander needed us,
we tried it alone,
and nothing was ever the same.
So...
maybe this is like a do-over.
Besides,
he's your father too.
I've been expecting you.
Confident, aren't you?
It's always the same look
when one covets a weapon.
I've fought battles from the Bloodcliffs
to the Dalamor Plain.
I've never seen a beast of such savagery.
No beast is more savage than man.
I trust you have terms.
You will serve me.
My enemies will be yours.
Your weapons will be mine.
In return, I will supply all your needs.
You will be treated
as an esteemed adviser.
But I demand absolute loyalty.
Do not test this,
or you will yearn for Caitlyn's dungeons.
You already know what I want.
He isn't a monster.
He was once a man.
Well respected, at that.
Victim of great tragedy.
He had a ferocious will to live.
An incredible tolerance for pain.
With him,
I was able to make strides
impossible with any other specimen.
But the mind...
The mind I could not recover.
The man forever lost
in the bowels of the beast,
compelled only by the scent of blood.
Or so I thought.
It now seems
I had yet to uncover the right catalyst.
Blisters and bedrock.
There was a funeral
for you in Noxus.
Oh. Did Mother commission a statue?
I held rites in Piltover.
She believes you're dead.
I do like to disappoint her.
How did you know to do that?
I don't know.
I just felt...
It's like some sort of puzzle.
Kino, what happened to you?
How did you wind up here?
She didn't tell you.
After a few rounds with
some dubious noblefolk in Basilich,
I started hearing strange rumors
about Mother.
Different than the usual kind.
They said, many years ago,
she passed through their hometown and...
fell in love.
That's not our mother.
Indeed.
But the more I inquired,
the more I started believing it.
The old travel logs.
The local accounts.
I should have left it alone, but...
The affair led to a child.
That's impossible.
It is the reason we are here.
Simply put,
whatever that child inherited
is of terrible interest to our captors.
This will allow you to locate your beast?
Not precisely.
My family archives
have shed light
on many of this city's mysteries.
Commander.
General.
One such mystery caught my attention.
The curious dismissal
of a revered academy alchemist.
Unparalleled, by all accounts.
And no mention of his crime.
This led to one other missing puzzle piece
whose absence has always
gnawed at my mind.
Who invented Shimmer?
We have our answer now,
don't we, Dr. Reveck?
You're a monster.
Why?
Why do all this?
Why does anyone commit acts
others deem unspeakable?
For love.
Perhaps,
in another life...
you would have been friends.
Everything I've done is to cure her.
I believe the beast may hold
the final key.
Precisely what are you trying to cure?
That affliction we all suffer.
Death.
Imagine a world
that no longer need fear it.
- Mel?
- I'm getting us out of here.
Hmm.
Say this is some sort of sordid labyrinth.
Usually there are consequences
for someone who fails these tests.
Deadly consequences.
I deserve to know the truth.
Of course.
Makes you wonder
why she kept this from you, doesn't it?
For all these years?
I'm missing something.
A healthy sense
of self-preservation, I'd say.
You aren't my brother.
Who are you? What have you done with Kino?
We had such high hopes for him.
At first, it seemed plausible
that he could have been the child.
But then your mother...
led us to you.
Sister.
What is it?
A message from Vander.
To Silco.
- "Silco, I've looked everywhere, but..."
- I've looked everywhere, but...
it's clear you don't wanna be found.
God, I'm shit at this.
I'm sorry.
When she died, I lost my head.
I told myself what I did to you
was for the greater good,
that you deserved it.
But the dirt was on both our hands.
Anyway, you know where to find me.
Blisters and bedrock.
V.
If he found this,
everything might have been different.
We have to get out of here.
It's him. It's Vander.
- That's not Vander.
- It is.
Something's got him riled up.
No, Vander, no.
It's me.
He's gonna kill you.
Don't hurt him.
Hark!
Vi, it's him.
You have to believe me.
Vander!
What's the occasion?
Hmm. Can't a lady
just be in the mood for a familiar song?
Not this lady,
and not this song.
Tonight a harebrained scheme
these two bozos cooked up
to turn a dank crack in the earth
into a thriving, healthy community
became a reality.
Tonight, eh?
You hear that, Bozo 2?
We made it. We're done.
Oh, you're sadly mistaken.
I'm Bozo 1.
A night of revelations.
I'm knocked up.
- A girl.
- How do you know?
Mm. Wasn't really part of my plan,
but guess that's everything
when you're living week to week.
What did Connol say?
I haven't told him.
Working up the nerve.
I don't know anything about kids.
I get sweaty being alone with one.
Hey, you're gonna be a great mother.
Shut up.
I'm not ready for that.
I started trying to come up with a name,
and it hits me that this one word
is a decision
she's gonna live with her whole life.
I can't protect her
from all the shit down here
and work out how to be a parent
at the same time.
Then I realized,
I don't have to.
Hmm? Why's that?
Because the second I told you,
I put you on the hook.
You two are gonna figure
this Zaun thing out.
I don't care if you have to carve it
out of the bedrock, covered in blisters.
You're not allowed to fail anymore.
For her.
For me.
What's the point
if we can't raise an ankle biter or two?
To Zaun, then.
Blisters and bedrock.
I've always liked the name Violet.
What are you waiting for?
He's your dad too.
Salo?
What are you doing here?
Jayce.
One could ask the same question.
How are you walking?
Who do you think could mend
such a broken creature?
Would you want to speak with him?
Jayce.
I'd feared I wouldn't have the chance
to speak with you again.
Viktor?
I would prefer to converse in person.
But there's so much work to be done.
How are you doing this?
I suppose this is
somewhat beyond where we left off.
Is Salo still in there?
Where else would I be?
You have my solemn vow
that anything you discuss
will be kept in the strictest confidence.
I owe Viktor...
everything.
Very kind, Salo.
I have so many breakthroughs
to share with you, Jayce.
I thought you were done with Hextech.
And me.
I was clouded by emotions.
Come. Visit me.
See what I've accomplished.
I've helped so many.
You've given Hextech
to the people?
As we always promised we would.
Viktor has truly worked wonders.
Hextech isn't a miracle.
It's a curse.
We have to end it, Viktor.
We have to.
You seem different.
Something happened.
Now I see it.
You, too, have touched the Arcane.
Your mind suffered.
If you'll excuse me,
I must return to him.
I can't let you leave.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
I'm sorry too.