Huh?
You're beyond help.
Whoa, relax, jumpy.
I've got a new idea...
Uh, did you just throw that?
Stay... Stay back.
Oi.
What in the seven sumps
is all this racket?
Oi, one of those days, huh?
You know those ugly twins,
genius and madness.
Maybe take the madness outside.
I still got a business to...
Oh.
What's gotten into him?
♪ I wake up to the sounds
Of the silence that allows ♪
♪ For my mind to run around
With my ear up to the ground ♪
♪ I'm searching to behold
The stories that are told ♪
♪ When my back is to the world
That was smiling when I turned ♪
♪ Tell you you're the greatest ♪
♪ But once you turn, they hate us ♪
♪ Oh, the misery ♪
♪ Everybody wants to be my enemy ♪
♪ Oh, spare the sympathy ♪
♪ Pray it away, I swear
I'll never be a saint, no way ♪
♪ My enemy ♪
♪ Pray it away, I swear
I'll never be a saint ♪
♪ Look out for yourself ♪
♪ We arrived
So we'll start the game ♪
♪ Start the game ♪
♪ Who is playing
When it all ends the same? ♪
♪ Don't take it so hard... ♪
Hey, spaceboy,
I'm not talking to myself over here.
What is up with you?
You've been out of it all day.
I feel like
I woke up in the wrong universe.
This is what happens
when you stay up all night.
Those synapses start firing around
like drunk slugs.
There's still plenty of time
before the competition.
Okay? We'll work out the kinks.
I've got you.
Ah, if it isn't Zaun's royalty.
My liege.
Sit down.
Hey, hey, little man.
Trouble in paradise?
Just the usual project woes.
Tell me about it.
We finally got the hybrids
to feed off the fissure gases,
but the conversion rate's way too low.
They hardly grow.
They're nowhere near robust enough
to purify all the air down here.
- Unless you plant a million of them.
- No way we're doing that.
And we've tried cultivating the soil,
infusing the water.
No luck.
I'll be right back.
Oh, no.
Go. Save him from himself.
Where would you be without her?
Hey, Gert.
No. Oh, come on.
- Hey...
- Hey, Gert.
Do the Chem Sisters
have another show coming up?
Mylo here is a big fan.
Like, huge.
Cool.
Uh, yeah, the old man's gonna let us
play the party the night before
that Innovators Competition
you all are gunning for.
What would they do without you?
There would probably be some arm-flailing.
You know, one thing I learned
as a bartender:
As good as it feels
to pour everyone's drink,
you need to fill your own cup
every now and again.
Let me guess.
You think I'm holding myself back.
I think you're too smart
to spend your life in a bar.
Hey, professor.
- Professor?
- Am I late for a gathering of the minds?
Whoa.
Oh.
One can't shout from the rooftops
about being thrust
into parallel dimensions
without awkward consequences.
It seems the anomaly which dislodged us
from our proverbial reality
also scattered us across time.
Man, I thought I was going crazy.
How long have you been here?
One thousand,
one hundred twenty-eight days,
six hours, and twenty minutes.
Give or take.
So you've just been waiting for me
all this time?
Precisely. Or rather, imprecisely.
I grew skeptical you'd arrive,
even during my unusually long lifetime.
What about Jayce? Is he here?
I fear he may have wound up elsewhere.
The anomaly behaved
differently around him.
Tell me you figured out a way
to get us home.
That is a veritable conundrum.
I'm afraid Hextech
was never invented here.
And without a creation
so prodigious as the Hexgates...
No anomaly.
Oh, it isn't all bad.
I've been able to accomplish
wonderful things in this world.
Give it time to settle.
This place will grow on you. You'll see.
Grow on me?
I have people back home who need me.
We don't belong here.
And yet we can't leave.
I'm gonna find a way back,
with or without you.
- Oh!
- Oh. Uh...
I was gonna go see Vi.
Vi?
You wanna come?
What have we done?
Hello?
Is anyone out there?
Who's there?
You.
Did you bring me here?
Where are we?
Wait!
No.
It can't be.
What's with
the third degree, Ekko?
We've been working on this for months.
Humor me.
You had one of your funky dreams
about an energy-storage device
that you swore would win the competition.
So you came to me for help.
I came to you?
You weren't gonna figure it out yourself.
"Zero-loss chemical energy cell."
And this invention.
You don't have
some alternative purpose for it?
You're the big idea guy.
Sorry, sis.
Someone's wigging out over his project
and having an identity crisis again.
No names.
I got the "not living up to my potential"
speech from Vander again.
Reminds me of you.
Hmm?
She's dead?
How?
That's not funny, Ekko.
It was a mistake to come here.
What's that supposed to mean?
Just 'cause you're having a bad day,
don't take it out on me.
Was it you?
You gave us the tip.
We went on that job because of you.
The job.
That's why there's no Hextech here.
You should leave.
Go. Before I do something I regret.
Believe me, I'm working on it.
♪ Hold me right now ♪
♪ To look back
And I've disappeared ♪
Come on. I saw it over here.
Care for a cup of tea, sir?
Come on.
♪ Go spin the wheel ♪
♪ And see where it lands ♪
♪ Join in the circus ♪
♪ Stay for a dance ♪
♪ And right when the war quiets down ♪
♪ Strike up the band ♪
♪ Keep marching on ♪
♪ My friends ♪
♪ And do what you can ♪
♪ Wait till your brothers
And your sisters ♪
♪ See where you been ♪
♪ And if you love the journey ♪
♪ More than the end ♪
♪ Go ahead ♪
♪ Just turn that hourglass around ♪
♪ And count to ten ♪
♪ This ain't goodbye... ♪
Violet, don't! Ple--
Please, no...
♪ It just began ♪
♪ March on, my friends ♪
♪ Whoa-oa-oa, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Go and make some mistakes ♪
♪ You live and you learn ♪
♪ And where the chips fall ♪
♪ Is not your concern ♪
♪ Like the wind gonna breeze ♪
♪ Fires'll burn ♪
♪ Just let the gears ♪
♪ My friend ♪
♪ Oh, just let the gears ♪
♪ Let them turn ♪
Thank you very much.
You think you can recreate the anomaly
with these?
That's the theory.
Inconceivable.
So you'll help me?
I meant that quite literally.
I don't believe this can be done.
Tampering with the Arcane
never ends well, lad.
The risk is far too great.
You said I was your pupil.
I need a professor.
Better yet,
a partner.
Oh, blast nozzles.
How could I forsake
a brilliant lad in need?
Again.
I never asked for this.
That research is everything.
My whole life.
He was my mentor, Mel.
And I betrayed him.
You must destroy it.
It corrupts.
Consumes.
I was trying to create magic.
- Piltover...
- It's your time now, Jayce.
Perhaps it's time.
No, no.
For the era of magic.
I've seen nations destroyed...
Please.
...exactly like this.
Watch your step.
We're almost there.
I don't know what this is all about,
but if you're trying to apologize,
dragging me through the...
You painted this?
I had this dream...
where things went another way.
She looks so badass.
You don't know the half of it.
She was the toughest person
in all of Zaun.
Nothing scared her.
No, not my sister.
Vi was strong because she was afraid.
Her fear of losing us
is what made her fight so hard.
- You were different in my dream too.
- Oh, yeah, buster?
Is that what this is about?
You want me to change?
No.
No, no, I just...
You aren't the kind of person who helps
other people with their projects.
Your ideas change the world.
I can't shake the feeling
that that's who you're supposed to be.
Things are good, Ekko.
I like my life.
I don't wanna lose what makes me "me"
chasing some wild dream.
Sometimes taking a leap forward
means leaving a few things behind.
You're a real mystery, aren't you, mister?
All right, out with it.
What do you want from me?
Hmm.
Huh.
It's so small.
Golly, we've done it.
Halfway there.
So, what does it do?
Uh...
You just asked me that.
No, I didn't.
I'm too tired for games.
It's a time loop.
Huh? A time loop?
- Huh? A time loop?
- A time loop.
You're going back in time.
Gadzooks. How did you stumble upon that?
I was playing with inversions
on Jayce's acceleration rune.
How far did you go?
I don't know. A second?
- Try going back further.
- Take it slow, lad.
We wouldn't want to push
a new invention too far too quickly.
Mm...
One.
Two.
Three.
- Gadzooks.
- Four.
The limit is four seconds.
Are you certain, my boy?
What were the indicators?
Trust me.
It's four seconds.
- Amazing.
- Hmm.
We could show it off at the party.
We aren't done.
Please go change before the party.
I think I might know
how to give it a boost.
A boost?
A momentary upgrade, if you will.
That's great. Where do we start?
You can start by attending your party.
One's thoughts are
more easily gathered in isolation.
And what's the point of a device like this
if you don't enjoy the time you have?
You load it through here
and then you wait for it...
It's just a prototype for now...
There he is.
Hey, nervous, kid?
Big day tomorrow.
It's all I can think about.
Where's the little lady?
Not sure. She said something
about making an entrance.
She does love a spectacle, eh?
Yeah.
Hey, in case I don't remember
to tell you tomorrow,
you've always meant the world
to me, Benzo.
Oh.
Well, you, uh...
Ach. Uh, you...
Oh, don't get all mushy on me now.
Hey.
- Making the big man misty, are you?
- Oh, these damned allergies.
You should be proud of yourself, Ekko.
Powder's been raving about your Z-Drive.
Can't remember the last time
I saw her so alive.
I have the feeling
that you'll be running this place soon.
So there's a chance for us yet.
You?
Didn't think
I'd miss your big day, did you?
Didn't you try to kill him?
Greatest thing we can do in life
is find the power to forgive.
Ach.
Some night.
It's beautiful.
Where'd you learn those moves?
Oh, I was just following your lead.
Mm.
He's got lines.
Hey. Uh...
I just want to thank you.
You know, for everything.
I used to dream
the undercity could be like this.
But somewhere, I got consumed
by all the ways it wasn't.
I gave up on it.
Gave up on you.
I've never seen you
give up on anything, Ekko.
You ever wish
you could just stay in one moment?
Sometimes taking a leap forward means...
leaving a few things behind.
I promise I'll never forget this.
You better not.
- Sorry, I...
- No...
It's fine, I...
Can we just pretend
like it's the first time?
Ekko, my lad. You're just in time.
This is a big upgrade.
Just a moment.
I only need
to hook up the final power supply.
Whoa.
This is where it all started, isn't it?
The end of Piltover.
Because of Hextech.
Why did you ever give me this?
Why?
It doesn't have to go this way, right?
Just tell me there's a chance.
Oh, I do wish
I could apologize to Ms. Powder
for co-opting her space like this.
It truly was the only way.
Send me back.
Never a dull moment.
I must say that since I've met you, lad,
I've truly lived.
What?
- Back in a wink.
- No! Heimerdinger, wait! Wait!
I won't fail.
I swear it.
No!
Powder?
Huh?
What happened?