SYMPATHY FOR THE DEVIL
Those who don’t work, don’t eat.
Go find your own food.
Me? I’m okay.
Women are grand by birth.
3 million…
Well, I’ll have the
guys earn it for me.
Damn, blues harp music is good.
It’s just as good as I thought.
I thought you were a fan of jazz music?
Don’t be stupid.
I even warbled when I was
sucking on my mother’s milk!
You were a pretty thoughtful kid…
No mistake, that’s Giraffe.
All right, I’m going from the right.
You go from the left.
There’s a fatso in the way…
That’s… Fatty.
The ball’s in your court.
Hey, Fatty!
Fatty River! Long time no see!
Oh! Who’d have thought, it’s Jet Black!
When the hell did you get here?
How about you? You look so easygoing!
Did ya catch a big one?
I didn’t know you were
a fan of blues music.
You’re kidding me.
I’ve lived only for the blues
since I was in my dad’s sack!
Give him back!
Zebra!
Hey you! Don’t die!
Hey!
Shit, are you going to
wipe out my bounty?
D-Don’t be fooled by his appearance…
You idiot! Don’t speak!
…him… Help…
…him…
This stone…
Hey!
I can’t say for sure
until I analyze it…
…but it might be worth a hefty sum…
So, what are ya gonna do?
Like I know?
He’s the one who gave it to me and
he’s the one who went off and died.
I see no harm in keeping it.
There is no harm.
After all, it’s not your
duty to help the kid.
This is gonna pay for our food.
There’s none for you.
You have such a poor heart…
I’m not like that.
Here, have a gift.
Oh, what’s this?
An invoice? What for?
All the expenses that you’ve
racked up on our ship.
Thanks for your business!
You’re welcome.
So why are you asking
about the dead bounty?
Well… uh…
So you were after Giraffe, too.
Ya got a good deal?
Go ahead, eat.
Ah well.
There’s no bounty in it anyway.
Yeah. No gain at all.
No, no. There really is nothing.
Ah well. You’ll owe me one for today.
You know that kid on the
blues harp the other day?
Giraffe was after
that kid Wen’s father.
His old acquaintance, Zebra.
Acquaintance?
You didn’t even know that?
That they were the top of the Volunteer
Self Defense Squad until ten years ago?
But why is he after an old comrade?
Ten years ago, Zebra and Giraffe
attempted to reclaim a certain facility,
But, a few days later,
Zebra ends up missing…
…and Giraffe finds himself blindfolded
in a weird place he’d never seen before.
Giraffe was going after the top spot
in the group, but he was betrayed.
But Zebra was still alive…
So, in the end, Giraffe was
killed by some form of betrayal?
Women easily betray others,
but men live for duty.
Duty, huh?
That’s what I’d like to believe.
Who are you?
Someone suspicious.
What do you want?
Giraffe asked me…
…to help you.
But Zebra shot Giraffe…
Yeah…
Then why did Giraffe tell
him to help the kid?
This kid’s showing up here, too.
He must be pretty famous.
Yeah. The kid’s a genius.
This guy isn’t Zebra!
What?!
Look… the date!
What the?!
Why the hell is this kid in an article
from 30 years ago with the same face?!
Come on. There’s nothing to fear.
Come over here.
Little twerps should stay outta this.
If you stick your neck
in too far, you’ll get burnt.
Don’t give me that
conceited crap, kid.
I ain’t a kid.
All kids say that.
I may look like this, but…
…I’ve been alive since
the days when humans…
…crawled only on
the face of the Earth.
It started on the day of the accidental
explosion of the hyperspace gate.
My body has ceased to age.
I can’t die.
The guys that took interest in me, and
experimented on me, all died before me.
The end for this guy started
when he snuck into the lab.
I needed a “parent” to use as a cover.
D— Don’t be fooled
by his appearance…
…him…
Help…
I think this was the third guy.
Now, gimme the ring.
Ring? What ring?
That’s fine…
Even if you had it,
it’s a pearl before swine.
Give me a break, you big klutz!
You’re lucky you got
away with this little…
…since we don’t have
the money for a funeral!
Sorry.
Knock it off, Ein!
Shut up.
Oh?
Jet, the alpha-catch.
Shit… this piece of junk…
All right!
Now… what are ya seein’?
The hotel.
He’s remembering the time
that Giraffe died.
Give him back! Zebra!
Come over here!
Shit!
And then what?
What did Giraffe say?!
I have it now.
I can do you in with this.
This is a stone that
will return time to you!
Now, hand Zebra over to me!
Zebra!
When the Gate exploded,
a vast amount of energy and…
…an imaginary coordinate system
were created from the…
…resulting twists in hyperspace and
got enclosed into the gem of this ring.
And that same energy broke
Wen’s circadian rhythm.
His pineal gland continually
produces a substance…
…similar to melatonin
that inhibits aging.
That’s how the theory
goes in a nutshell…
You understand?
Like I do…
I don’t either.
So, in other words,
there’s no way to make sure…
…other than to stick
that gem into Wen.
I don’t know what will happen.
It might explode the
moment you shoot it in…
This makes me excited.
What?
I thought this might be
the last time I’d see you…
…so I thought I’d see you off.
Oh, so you’re finally
going to leave us?
No, you aren’t coming back.
I don’t like it.
I don’t like it one bit.
Men are such idiots…
I see…
I can finally die now…
I feel so heavy…
But… I feel so at ease now…
Do you know?
Do you understand? Do you…
Like I do…
Aishiteta to nageku niwa…
Too much time has passed by…
…amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
…to lament that we were deeply in love.
Mada kokoro no hokorobi wo…
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart…
…iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
…cannot heal all the tears in it.
Kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
Honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is.
Doro no kawa ni tsukatta…
Sitting in muddy water…
…jinsei mo waruku wa nai…
…isn’t such a bad life…
…ichido kiri de owaru nara…
…if it ends after the first time…
COMING EPISODE
Hey, do you know
what heavy metal is?!
What?! I didn’t catch that!
Heavy metal, I said, heavy metal!
What did you say?!
Hey, can you do something
about this racket?!
This is running in the background
during the entire next episode!
Maybe I shouldn’t appear, then!
I can’t hear a damn
thing you’re saying!!
Next episode: “Heavy Metal Queen”!
HEAVY METAL QUEEN
Are you sure they
can really hear us?!
HEAVY METAL QUEEN
Are you sure they
can really hear us?!