WILD HORSES
Really, this just
doesn’t suit my style…
…to just sit and wait like this.
We pick our spot, then wait patiently.
That is the secret behind fishing.
Did you ever consider that maybe
this was the wrong spot?
The bait has no right to complain.
What are you fishing for?
“Starship Pirates.” A group that
calls themselves pirates.
Pirates?
A group of people that
like to attack a ship…
…and rob anything and
everything from them.
Like to rob, rob, drunken slob!
Besides, where the hell did Spike go?!
He left to overhaul his ship,
and still hasn’t…
Thanks.
But Spike… Man…
What’s he doing now,
without giving us a heads-up?
You’re late, Doohan!
Yeah! Go, go, go!!
Hey?
Hey!
Strike three! Batter out!
He just let that one slide by…
and that’s the game!
Man!
Why didn’t they just
send in a pinch-hitter?
Come on, Eightwood is getting old!
Don’t ya think?
Where’s Doohan?
The old man’s kinda busy right now.
I’m Miles, his assistant.
Nice to meet ya.
Man, they were really great when
they won the pennant 14 years ago.
They just kept hittin’ the ball one after
another, and turned losing games around!
Especially when Randy, Blanket,
and Hills hit consecutive homers!
I really wish you coulda seen it.
And ya know…
Hey, do people often say
you’re the silent type?
And people often say you
talk too much, right?
Kinda.
The… Swordfish, right?
The machine back there…
Yeah.
That’s the amazing mono-racer
that the old man built, right?
It’s just an old machine.
I don’t want it, but it’s a part of me.
I hear ya…
Us Blue Sox fans feel like we
fell for some wicked broad.
Really! I can’t remember how many times
I’ve thought about giving up on them!
Jesus, not again…
Yo, old man!
Yo. Long time no see.
Yeah.
Miles, where’s the checklist?!
It’s out there!
I put it on the ship’s body!
He’s been fixing that ancient thing?
I think it’s useless.
The computer isn’t compatible
with the mono-system.
Miles! Gimme the EV Transmitter,
the absorber for the main gear…
…and the three-eight pneumatic tube!
A three-eight?!
I don’t have something that special!
Order one from Reggie.
His place has them!
Yeah, yeah. You really
are some slave driver!
Some hobby!
Did we catch it?
It wasn’t me! Where is it?
It’s close! Shit, I used bad bait!
Hey!
This is a good machine.
Attacking blessed people like
them and giving to the poor…
…is human equality,
Don’t you think so?
Heh, heh, I get it.
This is what ya call social reform.
Yeah. It’s only right for us,
the poor, to take from them!
Something’s coming!
Cops?!
Hi.
That’s enough.
Bounty-hunter?
Harman.
Be a good girl and come here…
Faye, above you!
What the?! Is this a joke?!
It’s not me!
Ruth! One more behind us!
And it’s huge!
I know.
What a tattered old ship!
Leave me alone!
Abnormality found in the mono-system.
Booting the emergency pilot program.
Hey, stop this thing!
Like I know how!
Looks like he’s taken
you on quite a few spins.
Cut it!
The accelerator pump is all worn down.
I know.
And the fuel injector doesn’t
have a silencer on it…
Don’t need one.
But it’s noisy, and it trembles…
If you put one in, then I can’t
hear what it’s telling me!
Just hurry up and connect the injector.
First of all, a three-eight
isn’t popular anymore.
Why don’t you switch to
the new five-zero?
Miles.
And if you change the
navigation to full-auto…
…then you can glide
along without manual steering…
Do you want to use a machine,
or do you want the machine to use you?
Which is it?
I wasn’t exactly…
Just go!
You haven’t changed a bit.
At this rate, another assistant
is gonna leave you.
And you! The Swordfish wants
to run away from you!
I haven’t heard that before.
If you keep being reckless with her,
she’ll really throw you off someday!
Unfortunately, I’m not
one for delicate controls.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
I got something you don’t see often…
A three-eight pneumatic tube!
Yes, hello?
Oh, it’s you, Missing Man.
Where are you right now?
I’m still with Doohan. How’s Jet?
He seems rather busy right now…
Saying something about some bacteria…
Bacteria?!
A virus!
We got a computer virus!
Same difference.
Starting with the mono-system,
orbit calculator…
…flight path selector, engine
regulator, communications circuit…
…they’re all shot.
I don’t get it.
Gimme a simple explanation.
The computer broke and we’re
just drifting along!
Well, I understood that.
How about it? It’s the newest one.
You haven’t seen one floating
around anywhere else, right?
A mono-computer?
How about it? 150K… No, 100K.
A bargain, huh?
When it’s sold that cheap,
you lose money even on salvage.
So, who did it?
Where did you get this?
A truck? Any features?
A penguin…
…logo on…
…the delivery truck?!
Are you sure about the info?
Yeah. They apparently were
dealing at the Orbit Drive-in.
I see… nobody would be suspicious
of a delivery truck wandering about.
And how are we going
to counter the hacks?
Don’t get harpooned!
…and?
That’s it?!
They laughed this ship
off as “tattered!”
And they made that mess
out of my Hammerhead!
Unlike someone I know,
I always pay back what I owe.
What a wonderful principle.
I’m really not up for this…
I have an invoice from Doohan here.
Because they’re physically
sending the virus…
…they haven’t developed
a vaccine for it.
That is where this secret
weapon of ours comes in.
What? That’s just our
normal communicator.
If you get infected by the virus,
cut off the entire mono-system.
Then, all navigation and
communication will go down.
As I said…
I will navigate you with this.
Because this is set to the frequency
for an old communications satellite…
…it has nothing to
do with the mono-system.
Oh, another run scored
against the Blue Sox!
That’s some secret weapon…
It was a penguin, right?
Yeah. A purple penguin.
There are two of them?
Wait a minute, it might be
a real courier service.
It’s a matter of how to
figure out if they are legit…
That’s easy.
We fire a shot, and the one
that runs is the one we want.
This is the first time
I agree with you on something.
Y-You guys!
What are you gonna do
if they’re both real?!
They both ran?
We didn’t consider that option…
I’m trusting you with that one!
I have to pay them
back for yesterday, too.
Forgive us!
W-We’ll pay the parking fee!
This way?!
Spike! Draw them out!
It’ll be a mess if they,
let the virus go in there!
I know!
So, let’s see what ya got…
He’s here.
Waste of time.
He’s after the arm…
He’s not taking us seriously! Ruth!
Ready to go anytime.
Take that!
Welcome…
Excellent!
Bingo!
He’s holding up pretty well.
Cut off the mono-system!
I’m doing it!
That idiot cut off his mono-system!
Hey… George…
And he’s in Earth’s
gravitational field…
Old man! Here, here!
—This is pretty bad!
—Align the D7. Ya did it before, right?
Like I remember!
No good!
There’s nothing we can do!
You idiot! Hurry up and
do something about this!
Dammit… Move! Move!!
Falling… We’re falling!
Spike, I’ll be right there.
I’m calculating an
interception course.
Until then, somehow
keep control manually,
Even if everything was normal,
it’d be tough to get outta here.
I can see that.
And I just had it overhauled…
Oh, well. Whatever happens, happens.
Spike, above you.
Your tattered ship
looks like a goddess!
Shit, the virus…
Spike!
I’m still alive!
We have to start over!
No way! Old man, ya gotta be kidding!
Are you really gonna move
this ancient piece of…
Do you think I’d do this as a joke?
Don’t just stand there!
Hurry up and get me some fuel!
All right!
Spike, can you hear me?
I got a calculation.
It’ll take another 7 hours
for us to rendezvous.
Come on, you’re joking, right?
We’re too close to Earth. The orbital
paths I can take are limited!
Isn’t there a way for
you to just swing on by?
If I plunge in at this
angle, both the…
…Bebop and the Swordfish
will burn to nothing!
Jet…
I have some booze hidden
behind the fridge.
Feel free to drink some.
Something wrong?!
I’m outta gas.
Nothing I can do now.
How about I go there and tow you back,
in exchange for that booze?
I heard the conversation.
Give me the Swordfish’s coordinates.
Doohan?!
How the hell do you?!
Spike, I don’t care how ya do it,
but slow down using an air-brake.
Slow down?
If you slow down within
Earth’s atmosphere…
…the gravitational pull
will accelerate you instead…
…which will give you
enough speed to escape.
However, you have to maintain
the ship at a certain angle.
Too far either way,
and you’ll be…
…thrown out to the other
end of the universe.
Unfortunately, I’m not
one for delicate controls.
Spike…
I know you can do it.
I didn’t give you the
Swordfish for nothing.
Don’t you start crashing, either!
Maximum propulsion.
You didn’t have to force
yourself to come with me.
You know how Blue Sox
fans love to party!
Let’s go!
All right!
We’re flying…
We’re really flying!
Lower the nose by 0.6 degrees.
You’re in too deep!
Spike, you’ll burn to a crisp!
This is the last chance!
It went in! It went in!
That was perfect!
Doohan, you saved me.
Not quite.
Most of the heat-resistant
tiles have peeled off.
The temperature is rising…
T-The landing gear isn’t
coming down either!
Oh yeah, and the #2 nozzle
won’t work either.
What?! Is that for real?
What are we gonna do?
—We can’t land without them!
—Oh, well… Whatever happens, happens.
I knew I shouldn’t have come up here!
I’m still too young to die!
Aishiteta to nageku niwa…
Too much time has passed by…
…amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
…to lament that we were deeply in love.
Mada kokoro no hokorobi wo…
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart…
…iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
…cannot heal all the tears in it.
Kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
Honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is.
Doro no kawa ni tsukatta…
Sitting in muddy water…
…jinsei mo waruku wa nai…
…isn’t such a bad life…
…ichido kiri de owaru nara…
…if it ends after the first time…
COMING EPISODE
Next episode: “Pierrot le Fou”.
PIERROT LE FOU