Cute face for Mom.
- Cute face for Mom.
- Cute face.
Cute face.
Ooh, yes.
Where did he learn that?
He just, like,
did it on his own.
And then we've been
saying it, so...
We were like,
"Make a cute face."
so now he, like,
will do it on command.
Shake your head.
Mase, you know, we used to say
that to you all the time.
"Shake your head."
And then we would say,
"Say yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you
boot."
That was, like, when we brought
you home from the hospital.
I had no idea how to treat
- a kid like you.
- You put me in the
garbage and then you let me
poop in it.
Yeah, I should put you
in the garbage and let you
poop all over the place, so I
wouldn't have to deal with it.
And Mommy was like, "You better
figure this out; figure out how"
to handle this kid."
I was like, "I'm only 25!
I don't know what to do!"
- I want to yell...
- Stop it!
How would I know what to do?
How?!
Tell me, man!
We're gonna put him back in the
garbage can where we found him.
Right in Mom's... Mom's thing,
where you came from.
- Aah, Daddy!
- That's the garbage
- can?
- It's the Dumpster.
Let's snap before we
- take off.
- Yeah, totally.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- Good, thank you.
- I guess we'll sit here.
- Yeah, I'll sit
- next to you.
- I am, like, so excited
- to go.
- Kim, it's been a
minute since we've been in Vegas
together.
I'm really excited about it.
- Kimmy.
- Hi.
- How was the ride?
- I'm, like, so tired now.
Oh, yeah, I fell asleep.
It's, like, so annoying.
Stephanie, stand behind me,
'cause the back of my dress is
not it.
Like, my ass is so huge.
I still have, like, 25 pounds to
go.
The fact that I'm, like, doing
appearances, like, blows my
mind.
I was not even out of the house,
last time.
Last time, I had, like, 50
pounds to go.
I've definitely had my fair
share of the press just, you
know, attacking me over things
that they think are
inappropriate because I'm a mom.
Right before I got pregnant for
the second time, I posted a nude
selfie.
I mean, I was so proud of
myself; like, I had gotten in
such great shape.
But people had such a problem
- with it.
- I've watched 50
things on everything about this
today.
- Insane, right?
- That's the crazy
- part.
- It looked like I was
- wearing a bikini.
- Did Piers Morgan
- respond to you?
- He wrote, like, a whole
blog about why don't I try to be
successful with my clothes on.
Like, why don't you try to be
successful with your clothes
off?
It's actually really hard.
I'll never stop posting photos
that I like of myself.
If anything, I feel more
empowered.
Like, if you're not into what
I'm posting, don't look.
I don't pay too much attention
to it.
- You look divine.
- Thank you.
Is this your first...?
This is your first... yeah.
Yeah, that's why they're
gonna be, like, so annoying.
Ten years from now,
you're gonna be, like,
"Oh, remember when I went to
Vegas?"
- Totally.
- "10,000 people came
to see me."
This is my first real
night out since I had, you know,
my baby, so it's gonna be a
fun night with all my friends.
You do, like, spend so much time
prepping for a night out when
you, uh, are a mom.
I was able to, you know, put my
kids to bed, read them, you
know, their stories,
then go out, and, you know,
make it home before they wake
- up.
- Make some noise
for Kim Kardashian; Kardashian
in the right now!
What's up, kids?
I haven't been to Vegas for,
like, years, so I'm excited.
You guys have to show me a
good time.
What are you looking for?
I don't know.
Just seeing what kind of snack
- she has.
- How about a cookie?
- I'm scared to take one.
- Okay, this is
something that I rarely eat.
Kylie?
- Hmm?
- I'm making myself a
Pop-Tart.
Do you want one?
- I'm good.
- Hey.
- What are you guys doing?
- Making ourself at
- home.
- Making a Pop-Tart.
- Do you want one?
- A Pop-Tart?
- Yeah.
- You, who won't allow,
like, a plastic dish in
someone's kitchen, because God
forbid if it's not natural and
organic.
But I'm at Kylie's
house, and she had no healthy
snacks.
The only snack that sounded
- appetizing to me was a Pop-Tart.
- There's fruit right
- there.
- Yeah, there's lots of
healthy snacks.
There's tangerines...
Fine, I'll eat half
of the Pop-Tart, and then I'll
eat a pear, everyone,
so just relax.
- Eat a banana.
- Okay?
So, Kylie, I needed to
swing by, because I was down the
street.
What's going on with the
- stalker?
- He's out of the
- psychiatric ward.
- I know, but...
Is it the same stalker?
Yeah. It's a situation
where he didn't just get
released from the psychiatric
ward, I just found out that he
escaped from the psychiatric
ward.
And he really thinks that he can
just keep following her around
and coming to this community
and trying to get in.
- How crazy is that?
- I think we take our
security, like, really
seriously.
Kylie has had a few incidents
with stalker-type situations in
- the past.
- Oh,.
- What is it?
- This isn't funny.
- No, this is nuts.
- This is really weird.
"Will you marry me?"
She's 17.
There has been a
guy that's been following Kylie,
- and I am definitely worried.
- All right, you guys,
- I'll see you later.
- I'll see you at
- dinner.
- You know, we had a dog
that we got, like, one of those
Forbes-trained German Shepherds.
But you have to learn, like,
German commands, which you
could easily learn, like, five
things in German.
You need, like, a mean dog.
What do you think, Kourt?
- What?
- Do you think I should
get this German Shepherd?
How cool would, like, our photos
be, like, of me and the dog?
I can tell the dog to sit here,
- and just have the dopest photos.
- If Kylie's just so
concerned that her dog's gonna
make great photos, like,
she's definitely not taking this
seriously.
I just think she needs to be
careful.
You want to come for me, bitch?
- Come for me.
- Bring it.
It would be hilarious.
- Look what I have.
- Why do you have this
- already?
- Because I wanted
samples.
Would you like a gingerbread
- cookie?
- Not really.
Are you gonna see
the kids later?
I got Mason new clothes though.
- So cute. Is he into it?
- I got him a bunch of
vintage bombers, vintage
T-shirts.
I went to that What Comes
Around Goes Around, where,
- like...
- Oh, I need to, like,
brace you.
Kanye is going to shoot a music
video for this song "Famous."
And the people that the video's
about, it's, like, Amber Rose,
Ray J, Chris Brown, Rihanna,
- Taylor Swift and Caitlyn.
- Caitlyn.
- Caitlyn?
- Caitlyn Jenner.
There's nudity, technically.
There's sheets over everyone.
I think he's obsessed
with Caitlyn though.
He just, like, likes
people that do... that are
authentic, that do what they
want to do.
Well, he wasn't doing
what he wanted to do his whole
- life.
- Yeah, but now he is.
I am still trying to
understand the whole... feud
between Taylor Swift and Ye that
happened about this whole song.
'Cause I thought she knew about
it.
She did, but she was
acting like she didn't.
But didn't they...
Weren't they, like, recording Ye
when he was talking to her for
his, like, blog?
For... no, like, for,
like, a documentary one day.
Kanye, every time he's recording
an album, he always has
videographers with him 24/7,
recording everything.
So Madison Square
Garden... nobody never heard it.
- It starts off Rihanna voice.
- That's the first
- song you're gonna play?
- Yeah.
Know me best
I feel like Taylor Swift might
It's really important to
him when he was writing this
song "Famous" that he, you know,
spoke to her, and they knew it
was gonna be controversial.
The camera crew filmed him
speaking to Taylor and got their
whole conversation.
So, I think he definitely
really, you know, cared about
how she felt.
I think she got freaked out by
the reaction, and all of a
sudden she flipped.
So many fake things that go on.
- So many fake things.
- It's just too much.
- He's just over it.
- It's like, why bother?
Yeah, why bother?
I have to do Fergie's video.
It's about MILFs.
Fergie asked me to be in the
video, and I've got to get it
- together.
- Kylie... you know how
she always tags her freakin'
location.
Even the police
told her to stop.
We really got to do
something that's gonna, like,
- terrify her.
- You know someone
recorded you when you were,
like, upset.
- Someone has the audio.
- I don't care.
- Kim, where are you?
- Hey, I'm in here.
My God, look at
this place. Jesus.
This is like a... this is a
store, by the way.
We could open up DASH Home
Collection.
That's just, like, what
I can fit me now.
Wow.
What's up with you?
You're, like, hiding in here.
I am going over all of
my e-mails.
I'm, like, so tired.
I have a cover to shoot that I
think I have to go to New York
for for a day.
- All right.
- It's, like, a big one.
Also, I have to do Fergie's
video.
- It's about MILFs.
- What are you gonna
- do?
- I don't know.
It's, like, she just wants,
like, her-her group of friends
- in it.
- Oh, that's fun.
Fergie and I have been
friends forever.
We're hanging out one day, and
she was playing me her music,
and I loved the song "MILF
Money," so she asked me to be in
the video, and I'm so excited.
I'm so honored.
It's gonna be so much fun.
I wish I had, like, a few more
- months.
- You say that all
the time, but you look great.
And nobody thinks you don't
look great.
You're good.
Now, does your butt shrink when
you lose weight?
- Yeah.
- Is that what
happens?
I just can't believe it shrinks
- from the weight.
- Like, it goes...
Yeah.
I measured it today, so...
What, do you do it
by watermelons?
You're a beast.
You drink tap water.
- Good for you. Calabasas...
- It's not tap water.
Oh, my God, okay.
Damn, girl, you rich in this
house.
So, what, like, it's already
- filtered?
- I don't know.
The whole house has a system.
- Hello.
- You sound like
- Adele when you answer the phone.
- I sound like a what?
- Adele.
- She doesn't know who
- Adele...
- What is going on?
Um, so, Kylie... you
know how she always posts.
And tags her freakin' location.
- Yeah.
- So, she, like...
- Her signatures are wild.
- Has a stalker.
Even the police told her to stop
posting, and she's still doing
it.
Kylie is so huge on social
media.
I think she's, like, one of the
most followed people on
Snapchat, which shows your
location instantly.
It's just... it's not safe, and
I want to make sure that, you
know, she is careful.
Yeah, I remember this
guy used to show up to every
appearance of mine.
And he was, like, mentally
disturbed.
And it was, like, so scary.
- Like, if anyone knows, we know.
- I don't think she
- realizes that we know.
- It's just, there's
- a way to talk to her.
- Wait, so what are you
- gonna do?
- We really got to do
something that's gonna, like,
terrify her, 'cause she's
obviously not taking it
seriously.
I feel like she'll
only learn that way.
Like, she won't listen.
Like, any time we tell her
anything, she wants to do the
opposite.
Should we get her held
up at gunpoint and we can dress
- up like...
- No.
I mean us, not a real person.
No, that's too crazy.
That's the best form.
Okay, I'll call you back.
- Oh, my God.
- Bye.
There's new ones that I
haven't seen today.
Wait.
Hi.
Your eyes weirdly look big.
Yeah, my eyes look
bizarre, and I think
it's your phone.
Like, I thought the app was on.
So that's just what my eyes look
like?
Yeah.
We can't change that.
There's no filter for that.
- Hi.
- They have an audio
- recording.
- Shut the up.
- I'm not.
Wait, hold on, hold on, hold on.
It's Kanye, hold on.
- Oh.
- Hey, babe.
Um, so, you know someone
recorded you.
- Okay.
- Um...
He said, "Okay."
When you were, like,
upset about Taylor.
The guy recorded the whole thing
- and someone has the audio.
- Uh-huh.
And you just, like, are,
like, upset.
I don't care.
Like, I was mad.
Is that illegal for them to
record me?
- Not in New York.
- See, that's what I'm
- talking about.
- Not in New York.
- Not in...
- Yeah, so, what-what...
I mean, does it start to seem
unfair now?
I mean, if you think it's a big
deal, I'm gonna follow your
- lead.
- I don't think it's a big
deal.
It's just the way the perception
- is.
- Well, yeah.
All right, let me see
what the team wants to do and
says and all that.
Not that you care, but I'm just
saying I care what people think.
I'm just like, my full-time job
is your publicist.
Kanye definitely just always,
like, speaks the truth, says
what he feels, says what he
wants.
He has no filter, he just says
what he, you know, believes in.
And some people might not
understand that, and so, like,
he has a bad guy reputation.
If you want to do
something to help it out or fix
- it, I'm down.
- Maybe just, like, lay
off Twitter for a little bit.
Let me see what the team says.
Usually, you know, I always try
to stay neutral, and, you know,
really think about where Kanye's
coming from and just, you know,
definitely try to give, like,
moral support and input.
Don't you think, like, I have to
think smarter for him?
- Mm-hmm.
- 'Cause he's gonna say,
"I don't care."
The wife of Pablo?
- The wife of Pablo.
- You look so good.
I'm having so much fun
doing this video with the girls.
We pulled your car up here.
- What's on my car?
- Uh, what is on your
- car?
- Who did that to your
- car. Is that your car?
- I am freaking out.
Let's go look at it.
- Hi.
- Hi. How are you?
- I'm great.
- Nice to meet you.
- Oh, my goodness, who is
- this?
- This is my baby.
- What's his name?
- This is Beelzebub.
- Hey, welcome to my world.
- This is so cool.
B. Akerlund is an amazing
stylist, creative director.
She is doing the Fergie video.
So cool.
Love this.
I'm excited to meet with her
today and, you know, just see
what her vision is for me,
- 'cause I really have no idea.
- I mean, just to
give you, like, a general, like,
overlook of the video, we
really, like, want to, like,
lift up all the women.
If it's a woman breast-feeding,
or whatever they're doing, that,
I mean, they still look like
Vogue.
That's, like, so been my motto.
If anything, I felt, like,
sexier after becoming a mom.
I had a curvier body after
becoming a mom.
You can be hot and be a mom.
That's what the whole concept is
powerful moms.
And obviously you're one of
them, so we want to, you know,
showcase you and, sort of...
But I could show you.
So, we want you to have your own
"Got MILF" ad, which will, like,
pop up on the TV.
I don't know what speaks to
you the most as a person.
Like, if you had to explain
yourself in, like, three words
what would it be?
I hate describing myself, but...
I mean, I would definitely say
sexy is one of them.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I think, if I were
to do an ad like this, like, I
like the ones when the girls
are, like, wet and, like,
dripping milk on them, and,
- like, that vibe.
- Okay.
Should be in the shower.
Like, should we do a swimsuit?
- Yeah, I think so.
- Like, a special
- swimsuit that...
- Yeah.
Sucks everything in.
Do whatever you want with me.
- Okay.
- You know, just make me
look skinny.
Meeting with B., I definitely
know that I'm in really good
hands.
Like, she's got it.
Her references were insane.
What she's planning on having,
you know, custom-made is just
gonna look so good.
So I feel like this is gonna
be so major.
I'm-I'm really getting excited
now.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- I'm, like, obsessing.
I know.
It's gonna be so fun.
Well, you are in good hands with
B.
Uh, I can't wait to see what you
guys come up with.
- It's gonna be so good.
- She'll take the milk
shower, you'll take the milk
bath.
Okay, perfect.
- Yes.
- Perfect.
- Okay.
- Well, we'll get in a
bath together.
What are you gonna get?
- Salad?
- I have no idea if they
- have anything else.
- They do.
I mean, they have, like,
sandwiches and stuff.
I used to get a tuna sandwich
once in a while.
Okay, so while we're
at lunch, we're basically trying
to teach Kylie, like, a lesson.
And Kim... I swear to God.
Oh, it's Kim, speak of the
devil.
Hey.
So, Steph is gonna come and
- she's gonna set it all up.
- Oh, my God, that's
amazing.
Okay, we'll be there distracting
- her.
- It'll be so good.
- So good.
- Because Kylie has
been so casual about this
security issue, my sisters and I
decide to do a little prank on
her to give her a wake-up call.
I think Kylie needs to
understand that this is not a
- joke.
- We're gonna make sure,
like, when we walk out with her,
that we think, like...
That we're like...
- Like it's serious.
- And, like, make it
a serious thing, instead of
being like, "Ha-ha-ha-ha."
Right. She's not
gonna know, at this point,
- that it's us doing it.
- Yeah, we got to, like,
scare her into it.
She needs to take this
- seriously.
- Agreed.
I don't think it's a bad idea to
play a harmless prank on Kylie.
Hi. What a cute bag.
And hopefully, kind of scare her
a little.
I think just showing Kylie how
easy it is to reach her might,
like, rattle her up a little
- bit.
- Are you buying
- horny goat weed extract?
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
- Horny goat weed
- extract... what is this?
- Yeah, I saw...
I saw "horny" and I got excited.
And then I saw "goat."
"Goat" made me
- really excited.
- Yeah.
And the "extract" part, yeah.
Oh.
- Cute.
- I'm not surprised
Kylie is Snapchatting and not
concerned about our location
being known.
And so this is exactly why we're
- doing the prank.
- Okay, Kourt, we got
- to go.
- Okay.
- Ky... where's Kylie?
- Say what?
Oh.
This way.
Right over here.
- My car? You moved it?
- Uh, Kourtney, we pulled
- your car up here.
- What's on my car?
Uh, what is on your car?
Who did that to your
car? Is that your car?
Oh, my God.
I have no idea what's going on.
I am freaking out.
I'm just gonna wait till they
- take it off.
- Come here.
- Let's go look at it.
- Why?
'Cause, let's go see what it is.
- You only live once.
- No, you guys did this.
It was nothing about us.
Very funny.
I can't really understand why
Kourtney would do this.
The paparazzi are definitely
gonna release these photos.
It's embarrassing.
Kylie.
- So Kourt.
- Huh?
What were you saying about fast?
I said some guys
jerk it, so they can last
- longer.
- Yeah, but I don't
think there's anything wrong
with that.
I'm not saying there is at all.
We're going to Hef's
at 12:30.
What do you do if you
bump into Taylor Swift tonight?
I don't know Taylor
Swift; why do I care?
Call Kim.
Okay.
Hi.
Uh, whatever happened with the
- Taylor Swift video?
- The clip is so good.
So the line, when she said, "I
made her famous," or whatever,
I heard she told everyone at the
table, like, "Well, I mean, it's"
true, whatever.
Kanye totally, like, made me
more famous."
And so that's what Kanye came
- up with the line, but whatever.
- So why don't you...?
I'll put it out.
What's wrong with you?
Yeah, but it's
like, why... I don't know.
'Cause, like, why do you even
want to get into this battle?
I just wanted to, like,
kind of stay out of it.
Don't let Khloe post it.
No, don't.
I don't want any of us to get
- involved.
- Yeah.
- Okay, bye.
- Kourt, come here.
I don't really feel like saying
much, because the Taylor Swift
fans love her, and I'm all for
that.
And all I know is, I saw the
video.
I heard Taylor, and I think that
Kanye did the right thing.
So please Taylor Swift fans,
don't kill me.
Who did your makeup?
That's not okay.
I know how it is when people
are, like, attacking your
husband, and I know that Kim
feels that Kanye did the
right thing.
You don't have to do that as a
songwriter.
You could really just say
whatever you want.
It's so easy to just go ahead
and attack Kanye, 'cause they
already perceive him in a
negative way anyway.
I really hate that he gets such
a bad rap for everything.
I mean, what do you think about
the video?
It's just funny.
- Everyone's so full of.
- So full of
that it pisses me off.
- Three, drop, good.
- I've got to get it
together, and get myself in
shape for this "MILF Money"
- music video.
- Yeah, come on, come on.
What is going on with Kylie?
She felt, like, really
disrespected.
Well, we were
trying to get her to take it
- seriously.
- Well, maybe there was a
better way to show her that.
- Hello, Don.
- How your body feeling?
Fine, but you know my quad.
- Right.
- We got to just see.
Mm-hmm.
Mind right, body ready.
Mentally zone in, focus.
I'm gonna start doing the, uh,
upper body with me.
So just cushion down, when
the arms go down, light jump.
Let's go.
One, drop.
Two, perfect.
Three, drop.
Good, four.
That's the pace I want.
Five, don't speed that up. Six.
I've got to get it
together, and get myself in
shape for this "MILF Money"
music video.
I'm really nervous though.
But if Chrissy can do this, and
she had a baby two weeks ago,
I definitely can get it
together, like, four months
later.
Four, cushion.
Five, cushion.
Let's go.
One, drop, up.
Two, drop.
Squeeze the arms.
- Good.
- You know, with Kim,
she just, like, you know, puts
being a mom first, but she takes
time to work out, eat well and
just feel her best.
Oh, the roll down.
Let me see this.
- Let's see it.
- I remember those days.
- Good job!
- Yeah. Come on, come on.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Hi, Reigny.
What are you doing?
Give me a little kiss.
Show me the face.
Did he do it?
Yes.
You're so cute.
How come you're so cute?
Show me the face.
Your mama used to do that.
Yeah.
You're so cute.
So what is going on with Kylie?
She was so upset.
Called me, hysterical, crying.
Said she never wanted to go out
and hang out with you guys
again, because she felt, like,
really disrespected.
And then we were
walking out to the car.
It just was a bad day.
There was so many people around,
so many paparazzi, and so I
think she was just like, "What's"
going on?" and then I was like,
"Come on, let's go to your car
and see it."
You know, I think she's
just young still and trying to
do so much, and she's got so
much on her plate.
It's still a really new, big
world for her because she just
turned 18, so she's got this
world of responsibility that
she's trying to get used to.
One of the things that's
stressing her out, and she
doesn't really talk about it at
all, is the whole stalker
situation.
She's had to change her whole
computer system, she's had to up
her security, hire more
bodyguards and get a new phone.
It's a lot to go through when
someone starts threatening your
existence and just the way you
live your life.
Everything had to change.
Well, we were
trying to get her to take it
- seriously, so hopefully she is.
- Well, maybe there was a
- better way to show her that.
- I do feel bad that
our idea to teach Kylie about
posting her location, you know,
it kind of freaked her out,
especially with so many people
around.
Everything about it went wrong.
And so, clearly, that was not
the best idea.
I just want you guys to
watch out for her because she is
the baby, and just be sensitive
to, you know, the fact that
- she's still growing up.
- Yeah.
Next time just get some
Silly String and call it a day.
Mm, sure.
- Hello.
- Oh, my God, you're
getting skinnier and skinnier.
Don't eat those cookies.
You won't... you don't need...
Like, you look so good.
Here, I'll split the difference.
I don't want it.
Why... that's how I know you're
not a real friend.
Real friends don't give friends
Vienna wafers.
I'm so nervous about the
Fergie video.
It's, like, called "MILF Money."
So it's gonna be, like, us,
like, walking with the big pram
strollers, like, down the street
in this neighborhood, and I'm
gonna be in, like, a "Got MILF"
ad, and then there's, like, a
diner, and then there's, like, a
- beauty salon, and...
- How cool.
There's, like, different
scenes, all with MILFs.
Well, you definitely
are a MILF right now.
- What other MILFs are in it?
- Chrissy Teigen.
Oh, duh.
That's fun that you guys all get
- to do that.
- Um, yeah, it'll be
really fun, but I have, like,
such anxiety.
You're really a crazy person.
You look so good.
I think better than you did
- before you had kids.
- I definitely am not at
my weight goal yet, but since
Fergie and I were friends before
we had kids, and now our kids
are friends and have playdates,
we totally get the mom struggle.
We get how hard it is to really
work out and feel good about
yourself again.
So I'm proud to be a part of
her, like, mom MILF pack and
music video.
I love the, like, message behind
it, and I would never miss it
for the world.
I mean, I think it's just, like,
we both, like, think it's, like,
super empowering to, you know,
have kids and then, like, still
be a hot, sexy MILF, you know?
There's, like, the mommy-moms
- though that, like...
- Kourtney, at first,
- was the mommy-mom.
- Totally.
After Reign, she's
like, "I'm gonna be a MILF."
- Totally. She's a MILF.
- Thank God. I thought
- we lost her to the mommy-moms.
- Yeah, me, too.
I'm gonna FaceTime her again.
So I just have a
The first time I
FaceTimed you, was your phone
- near you?
- No, I didn't know
FaceTimed me. When?
I like your acting
abilities; you're good.
It was honest.
What are you doing?
Looking at this MILF.
Seriously, she looks so good.
- No joke.
- That is not a good
- angle, sorry.
- It's all good.
- Well, she...
- No, she's the
ultimate MILF.
She looks amazing, but that...
And I'm just keeping it real...
That angle was not what's up.
- Um...
- Love you. Got to go.
Hey.
So do you... yeah, do you want
hair up in, like, the rollers,
or do you want it, like, softly
- out and then we tie the bandana?
- We need va-va-voom.
We need pinup.
Should we give her a moosh?
A little beauty mark?
Chrissy has normal
hair and makeup.
I think we should, like,
try to, like, really make it
look normal Kate Moss-y hot.
Vogue.
Your brand.
Just be concerned about your
- brand.
- Like, thank God Kanye is
here, because he definitely says
what's on his mind, and he's
definitely not feeling the,
like, blonde wig with the red
lips.
I'm actually, like, happy that
he even said something, 'cause I
wouldn't have had the balls to.
So should we
just do our own thing?
I think so.
GQ.
And she was like, "What about
when Kanye said him and Taylor"
might still have sex?"
I just don't care really anymore
and I'm gonna say how I feel.
So wild.
Walking up, walking up.
Make a hole guys, coming in.
Make a hole, please.
- Hi, babe.
- Hi.
How are you?
You look so good.
- Oh, yeah.
- Is that the diva Chrissy
- over there?
- Yeah.
- Such a diva.
- I know.
She's been giving all day.
All right, here we go, team up.
All right, guys, can I...
Everybody start moving back.
Thank you, thank you.
Roll it!
- Rolling!
- And playback.
There we go.
People always say the
word "MILF," and, you know, you
definitely hope that you become
one.
And everybody cleared off set.
Here we go, guys.
I feel like this song
and the message is just all
about, like, empowering women.
Once you become a mom, they want
to feel sexy, they want to feel
powerful, they want to feel like
they got their together.
They can be the best mom, have a
great career, be a great wife,
and that they just can do it
all.
Oh, my gosh, it's so beautiful.
- It's so beautiful.
- All right,
- let's rock it out, guys.
- I'm about to get in
this shower with you right now.
I'm like, get me in.
I want to touch.
And we're
rolling; play one.
Yes.
- Cut. Money.
- Kim Kardashian, it's
a wrap!
MILF!
Yeah, you really know what
you're doing on these sexy
shoots, girl.
I really have no idea.
Yeah, you do.
Babe.
- Thank you.
I cannot wait to see this.
Thank you so much for
everything.
- We'll text you about this.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Love you. See you later.
- You, too.
See you later.
Good stuff.
- Bye.
- Yup.
Cosmo interview coming up.
Do you get nervous for them?
I never did.
I'm like, "Why do I care?"
Yeah, who cares?
GQ.
- How was it?
- It was good.
She asked me questions like
Rob and Chyna, random O.J.
questions that no one really
asks me, but maybe 'cause that
show came out.
My publicist is gonna die.
She asked me how do I feel when
Kanye, like, raps about having
- sex with other girls.
- Mm-hmm.
GQ.
The interviewer straight
up asks me, like, how do I feel
that Kanye talked about having
sex with Taylor Swift.
I kind of just was really
truthful and said how I felt.
I never talk about
anyone, like, publicly, like,
especially in interviews, but I
was just like, "I've so had it."
I just felt like I wanted to,
like, defend him in it.
- Mm-hmm.
- 'Cause it's like, she
legitimately...
quote, says, "As soon as I get"
on that Grammy red carpet, I'm
gonna tell all the press, like,
I was in on it."
And then she just
- didn't like the reaction?
- Yeah, and, you know,
just another way to play the
victim.
Definitely got her a lot of
attention the first time.
I just don't think that he
should be punished for it still
to this day.
I feel like I've had it with
people blatantly treating my
husband a certain way and making
him look a certain way.
Kanye is always so honest and
speaks his mind, and, you know,
when we were first dating,
everyone would talk and
he always had my back.
At this point, I really don't
give a, so I'll do
whatever to protect my husband.
Yeah, Kanye, you know,
definitely, like, hurt her years
ago when he did that, and it
wasn't meant to be personal.
It could've been anyone.
'Cause, like, we all know that
"Single Ladies" was the biggest
- song of the year.
- Yeah.
So I think when she
didn't win, he just wanted to
- stand up for it.
- I'm so glad that
- you said the truth.
- Yeah, I'm just, like,
speaking the truth.
Like, he called her, spoke to
her.
She even helped him, like,
- rewrite.
- Yeah.
- It's so wild.
- What if you just called
- Taylor up?
- I'm just over it.
At this point, like, I know the
truth.
- Thank you for your advice.
- You're welcome.
But I'm not gonna take it.
You are so gorgeous.
I'm so lavender.
Is my boob hanging out the
- bottom?
- You are so
- gorgeous.
- You look so cute.
No filter?
You didn't...
I put a filter on it, you freak.
Oh, thank God.
I love your hair.
- Is my boob hanging out?
- No.
- I think lavender's your color.
- I think white's
- your color.
- What's going on?
Um...
I just wanted to apologize for
that prank.
- Mm-hmm.
- I just don't think
that we realized, like, what a
scene... I feel like we should've
known the second we got there,
and there was, like, thousands
- of people outside.
- It was just too many
- people.
- It was too much to
do that, so we should've, like,
stopped it.
The restaurant to the
car situation when there's too
many fans and paparazzi is
already stressful.
And then the
balloons, and the guy was
videoing, and then, like, you
just, like, weren't sure, like,
who was in on it.
Like, it was just too much.
So, I just wanted to say sorry,
but I think it is, you know,
important to, like, take it
seriously with the stalker.
My new thing is, like, if I'm
out public with the snapping,
like, I'll turn to airplane mode
and then you post them later.
I always do that.
I take it seriously.
Good, yes, good.
I'm just not trying to
be, like, a hermit my whole
life, you know?
They can't stop me.
We can't be scared of these
things.
But I appreciate you being
concerned and apologizing.
Even though Kylie
is my younger sister, she's 18
years old.
I think sometimes we do forget
she is a mature adult.
We don't give her enough credit.
She is really smart, and I
realize she wouldn't put herself
in a dangerous situation.
She's being cautious, and I'm
really proud of her.
- Ah, this angle.
- Oh, it's a video.
- Hi. Hi.
- Where you going?
- You're going to London?
- For the day.
- Why?
- Because Kendall had a
really awful night last night
flying to Paris, 'cause she gets
- really bad panic attacks.
- Oh, come on.
- And anxiety.
- Seriously.
I don't know what to do.
Wait, isn't it so funny
that people think Saint, like,
doesn't exist or something's
wrong with him 'cause I don't
- show pictures of him?
- I need to come over...
You need to move back here.
Enough is enough.
- Relax.
- No, I am.
I'm loving life.
Oh, my God, with Taylor Swift's
- team...
- How did this all start
- up again anyway?
- Just because I did an
GQ.
That's sitting
- right there?
- Yeah.
Thanks, you didn't read the
article.
- No.
- Well, if you had, you
- would've known.
- What would happen if
you just called Taylor up?
And just say, "What... just",
you know, what happened?
How did this go so south?"
How did this all start
up again anyway?
Just because I did an GQ.
That's sitting right there?
Yeah.
Thanks, you didn't read the
- article.
- No.
Well, if you had, you
would've known.
What would happen if
you just called Taylor up?
And just say, "What... just,
you know, what happened?"
How did this go so south?"
I just, this is what I don't
understand, because truly I
really do like her, and I really
like her team, and I really like
her mom.
I guess I don't understand the
motivation to...
- flip so quickly.
- Me neither, especially
'cause Kanye went, like, so far.
Like, no rapper is gonna call
someone that they're, like,
rapping about and get their
- permission.
- Yeah.
Like, he really wanted
to just, like, because they've
had their issues in the past,
like, he really did want to do
- the right thing.
- And be respectful.
Maybe she just took it the wrong
way.
I mean, at this point,
I'm just over it.
Like, yeah, am I annoyed that
people try to pin my husband as
this bad guy to, like, take
advantage a little bit?
But, at this point, like, I know
the truth, I know everyone
around me knows the truth, we
all do, so it is what it is.
You know, there's nothing we can
really do about it.
My advice is that you
give Taylor a call and try to
- make amends.
- Thank you for your
- lovely advice.
- You're welcome.
But I'm not going to take it.
Keeping Up with the
Kardashians...
Are you excited for Cuba?
It feels like we're in a dream.
Dorothy, you're not in
Canada anymore.
- Canada?
- Hey, Kylie.
- You look so cute and pretty.
- All my sisters are in
Cuba, and she doesn't know what
to do with herself.
Mom, you're acting a
little crazy.
- Okay.
- He was, like, waiting
for me to leave town.
I've been trying to contact
Lamar, but I am unable to.
Definitely makes me nervous.
Captioning sponsored by
BUNIM-MURRAY PRODUCTIONS