Mm-mm-mm
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Uh, yeah
I'm lonely
So lonely
With nowhere that feels like home
I'm lonely
So lonely
With no-one to call my own
Ah, yeah
Don't wanna be here no more
No more
Nobody knockin' at my door
Well, I don't wanna lie awake at night
Cos everything I do...
Yeah.
...Never turns out right...
Do that again.
...I'm lonely, won't you come on home?
PHONE RINGS
Hey, Maxxie.
Happy birthday, mate.
You fucked up my dream, Max.
What was it?
Oh, the usual. Russian virgins.
'Good Muslim boys don't dream about virgins.'
That's where you're wrong, Max.
That's all we dream of.
- Will you come to my birthday party, Max?
- Will you tell your mum and dad I'm gay?
I dunno.
I can't unless you do.
Maxxie, it won't be right if you don't come.
'17. It's the year of telling the truth. OK?
'The truth, yeah, mate?'
PHONE GOES DEAD
...Yeah, so lonely
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Ah, yeah...
- (All) Happy birthday!
- Agh!
SCREAMING
Mum! Get out!
That's tiny.
Get out! Oh!
Mum!
A respectful boy
at least wears something in bed!
Happy birthday, little boy!
I'm 17, Mum. I'm not a little boy any more.
So it would seem.
Now hurry up,
everybody's waiting downstairs for you!
"Dear... Cassie."
"Hi... Cassie."
"Hey... Cassie."
Oh, bollocks!
"Cassie."
"Dear Sid...
"It isn't easy to tell you this,
so that's why I'm writing.
"Don't try to ring me
because you're not allowed to here,
"and anyway, I don't want to speak to you
"and there's nothing you can say
to change this."
"I'm shit with words.
"Everything always comes out so... crap.
"But I've been thinking
and everything is getting clearer."
"My mum and dad have decided
that things aren't working out.
"So we're moving to a place called Elgin.
"It's in Scotland and everyone's happy there."
"The thing is, Cass, I've woken up this morning,
"the sun's shining through the window
and it's making me think of you.
"Cassie, it's not right you hiding away
in that clinic. You've got to get out in the world!"
"They're coming for me tonight
"and then I'll be gone and we won't
have to play this game any more."
"Cassie, I don't care if you think you're odd
"because I feel like singing when I see you
and you're beautiful.
"I've been such a fucking chapstick
these past few weeks
"and all I want to do now is sit on Brandon Hill
"and hold you and tell you
how wonderful you are
"and stick my hand down your knickers."
No. Jesus! "And..."
"I want you to know I really liked you, Sid."
- "And..."
- "But it's too late now.
"Goodbye."
I love you.
DOORBELL
Ange, there's someone at your door.
Yeah.
DOORBELL
Angie? Are you ashamed of me?
Of course I'm fucking ashamed of you!
Tut, Pussy! Right, I'll tell whoever it is...
No! Just stay there.
For Christ's sakes!
Oh, Christ!
Angela!
Merve?!
When did you get back?
Now!
Merve, you can't just do this.
We need to talk.
Angela, you know you missed me.
This isn't fair!
Where's your ring?
I threw it in the fucking harbour, OK?
FOOTSTEPS ON STAIRS
Angie? What ring?
CHATTER OF FEMALE VOICES
- Where were you?
- Sorry. Slept in.
Slept in? You miss prayers
with an excuse like that?
Dad, it's my birthday.
Aren't you going to say hello?
I've been on control
since three o'clock yesterday.
32 cabs, not that you'd care.
It's a stupid fuss over a birthday party.
Does it give respect to God?
Does it promote peace?
- No, Dad.
- Does it help the poor? It's an affront.
So why do we have to do it anyway?
I don't even want a party.
Because I love that woman
more than these legs I drag myself along on,
and what she wants, she gets. All right?
< Is Maxxie here yet?
Um... no.
We don't see him these days.
We had a fight.
A fight? You fight with your friends?
Yeah.
What would you fight Maxxie about?
He's a good boy.
Always well turned out,
respectful. The best type.
Never mind.
Whatever it is, forgive him
and don't be a bloody fool.
Now tell them I'm sleeping, huh?
- (Mum) Put down that food!
- (Child) Auntie, can I have one?
No, you can't! Get out of my kitchen!
Who's that boy?
All the time there's little boys.
Boys don't... Here he is!
(All) Happy birthday!
Hi, Auntie Jess.
Oh! He's got a moustache.
Little Anwar's got a moustache!
That ain't all Little Anwar's got.
Why aren't you saying hello
to Aunty Sahra and Uncle Muneer?
Sorry.
HE SHOUTS
They've come all the way from Sutton Coldfield
and they don't get a hello?
Hello, Uncle Muneer.
Anwar. So... 18 at last, huh?
No. No, I'm 17.
What?
He's 17?
Yeah. What's the problem?
You drag me here, all this way!
I paid money to drive on the M6. Money -
just to drive on a road
to come to a 17th birthday party? Huh?!
Ahh! Got you!
- I had you going, didn't I? Didn't I?
- He is so funny, my brother!
(Mum) Why did you fall for that one?
(Every fucking year!)
L-O-L-L-I-P-O-P.
Lollipop.
- You're just too good.
- Of course!
- When are your folks coming?
- Later. They've packed.
Hm. Bummer.
- You wanna get out of here?
- Huh?
Let's go out.
- We're not allowed.
- Come on. I want one last look.
What if we get hungry?
There's... there's food out there, you know.
Come on!
How?
It's easy.
We're just getting a breath of fresh air.
My friend thinks she want to puke.
Go. For fuck's sake, go!
HE PANTS
- Hello?
- 'Restorations Clinic.'
Can you help me?
I really, really need to come in.
I know you don't like it,
but I need to come in, OK?
Hello. Can I help?
Yes. Yes. I need to see someone.
It's very important.
There's something
I have to get off my chest
and if I don't, I'm afraid everything
might just totally go to shit.
Right.
I've got something going on
and I need to see someone.
I've got something going on in here...
(T-shirt) 'Megadog's trying
to tell us something. Woof, woof!"
OK. Let's see if we can sort you out, shall we?
Just you wait right there.
Ah, thanks.
I don't know what this means, but...
What? What's going on?
What are you doing? Let go! Come on!
You don't understand! Cassie-ie-ie!
HEAVY DOOR SLAMS
Hey!
I'm not mad, for fuck's sake! I'm fine!
I'm fine!
LIGHTER CLICKS
For fuck's sake!
PHONE RINGS
- 'What?'
- Leave him alone.
'What the fuck, Angie?! What the fuck?'
- Hey. Hey, I wanna talk to you.
- Talk away, sweetie.
Are you gonna tell me who the fuck you are?
- I'm the fiance.
- No, you're not.
- Yes, I am.
- Since when?
Since she asked me to marry her.
Where the fuck did you come from?
I'm Mervin.
She gave me genital herpes.
I'm the love of her life. I'm back.
You don't stand a chance, kid,
not even with that beautiful little cock of yours.
What, she told you?
She tells me everything, kid.
I can see into her soul.
Now do us a favour and disappear, OK?
But... No. She can see into my soul.
- How old are you?
- 17.
You haven't got a soul yet.
With luck you haven't got herpes, either.
Quit while you're ahead.
And with that, I bid you good day.
Hi, Effy.
Your brother just called me.
We're not speaking.
I heard things got a bit out of control last week.
You feeling better?
Is that why they sent you to the posh school?
They think that'll sort you out?
School on a Saturday.
Hardcore.
Why don't you speak, Effy?
Does nobody ask you why?
It must mean something.
Doesn't anybody care?
Tony really hurt me, Effy.
Why did he do that?
Sometimes I think you're the only person
in the whole world Tony truly cares about.
I thought maybe...
maybe he told you why he did that.
If I could trust him to tell the truth just once,
then maybe I could...
It was nice seeing you, Effy.
I'm glad you're OK.
- 'I love you, Tone!'
- 'You're going to be on Big Brother, Nips.'
- 'You do that and I'll kill you!'
- 'You're gonna be famous.'
'But if you're famous
you have to have, like, huge boobs
'and blonde hair and I have neither of them.
Would you like me like that?'
'I like you like that, Nips.
'You've gotta do something whacky.
'What?'
'Come to bed with me. Please.'
MICHELLE SCREAMS
- 'I'm sorry! I'm sorry!'
- 'Give me that phone!'
- 'What?'
- 'Go on!'
'Nips, Nips, calm down...
Calm down, Nips.'
RINGING TONE
Answer. You know you want to.
'Hi. This is Michelle.
Leave a message, except if you're Tony,
'because Tony can fuck off!'
BEEP
Please.
Goin' out of my mind
Tryin' to kill time
Wishin' the day away
Goin' out of your head...
DISCO MUSIC PLAYS
(Anwar's mum) Hurry up. Make sure you set up
all the tables and everything.
The caterer's going to be late, I know.
I see you're ready to party down
You're gonna have some fun tonight...
< GIGGLING
...You know the good place to go in town...
(Anwar's mum) What are you giggling about?
"Anwar, you naughty boy,
I want to spank your..." Who wrote this?
FEEDBACK SQUEAKS
Who wrote that?
Mum, why does Uncle Muneer
have to do the disco again?
Why on earth not?
It's just... Mum, please.
Are you hearing this?
He doesn't want my own brother's gift of music.
Do what your mother says, ungrateful wretch!
- But, Dad...
- Your uncle knows what's respectable.
- Dad!
- Your English friends have no restraint.
They don't wear enough clothes. They drink,
shout, fornicate. They puke in the back of cabs.
We have proper, tuneful music,
so the English don't burn the place down
and get me arrested.
That's why your mother is right in all things.
Now say no more about it. No more!
Thank you, Istiak. Thank you very much.
Come on, you three, now.
Is the buffet going to do itself?
Muneer's an arsehole.
What did you just?
A complete tosser.
At least he can't grope the women up there.
FEEDBACK
- Ladies!
- Hello, Mr Kharral.
Nicely dressed too. You see - respectful.
I keep asking Anwar
when Maxxie is coming.
He says they fought.
Why would anyone fight a boy like Maxxie?
Well...
I never see Maxxie, you know. He was
such a wonderful dancer. Tap dancing, huh?
- Superb. Physical.
- Yeah. We know...
Anyway. Have some fun, huh?
...Put on your high-heeled shoes and dance
You can be the queen tonight
Dressed in white
You will blow their minds
All eyes on you when you...
I won't be long.
Cool. But hurry, in case I get hungry.
I could hold your beautiful hands...
RINGS DOORBELL
...And kiss your beautiful eyelids...
< Oh! Hi, Cassie, come in.
- Sid's not here.
- I know.
...Throw open your beautiful doors
And phone your beautiful friends
But it's all over
It's all over...
Bye.
...It's all over
It's all over
I could bind your beautiful wrists
Oh, shame on your beautiful friends...
Oh, shit!
...Cos it's all over
It's all over
It's all over...
'So let's take a look at what's going
to be happening in New South Wales.
'It's going to be hot, super hot, and you'd
better keep in the shade around noon,
'because, by golly,
it's going to hit 42! Whooo!
'Ah, you've caught me off guard.
Thanks, Burt (!)
'...Flushing those pesky beggars
from underneath your porch.
'Showers will carry on till Thursday,
so get your bowsers out, guys.'
You're gay.
'Now let's take a look
at what's cooking down in Tasmania
'and believe me, whooo...'
CLICK!
DOOR SHUTS
- I broke in.
- That's not fair, Chris.
You lied to me.
I never lied. I just...
Merve went away on a field trip
to Alaska for six months.
Climate change.
What? He doesn't like hot weather?
No. Climate change!
- The fucking icebergs are melting, OK?
- Oh...
Christ!
Did you ever pay
any attention in college, Chris?
We're trying to fucking educate you!
Well, cheers, Angie.
Appreciate it.
We had some issues...
Well, Merve did.
And I...
Screwed around.
You don't know what I did.
You really don't know
that much about me, Chris.
I need some time.
Can't you see it?
What?
We've got some stuff.
We've got some stuff...
I'll see you, Angie.
Can't take it, huh, sweetie?
(Oh, yeah.)
Beat it.
DISCO MUSIC
Hi. Enjoying your party?
Um... Do I know you?
I'm Seeta... friend of Atifa.
Oh. Right, um...
Have I met you before?
Like a million times.
I asked your sister to invite me here tonight.
Right... Why was that?
(I want to tongue you senseless, big boy.)
Just to check... you're not my cousin, are you?
No.
You're not related to me in any way.
Uh-uh.
Happy birthday, Anwar.
(Thank you, Jesus...)
RECORD SCRATCHES, FEEDBACK
(Muneer) Welcome, everybody,
and a happy birthday to Anwar!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
He's the apple of my sister's eye,
a great God-fearing lad.
So we've thrown a party
to celebrate his birthday
and his marriage to his cousin
who's just flown in from Pakistan!
GASPS AND HUSHED MURMURING
Aaaah!
Got you!
Had you going!
Didn't I? Didn't I?
I'll bloody kill him! I'll kill him!
So come on, everybody, let's dance!
MUSIC STARTS UP AGAIN
Oh, yeah! All right!
Here we go, whoo-whoo!
Come on, everybody, hit the dance floor.
Come on, whooo-whooo!
Some say
Put some away for a rainy day
But I don't care what they say
Cos life's too short for me...
Raas!
This is a big boy tune!
This mofo's got some
serious riddims kickin' off!
You get me?! You get me?!
I'd so would love you to dance.
Would you?
I'd take the money, believe me, honey
I'd take the money
Why don't you come with me right now?
Sometimes
I find myself in a state of mind
Where I could live with the daily grind
But I'll never live that way again
Gonna party to the end...
Oh, God!
Oh, God! It's wonderful!
That's cool. I'm glad.
I think there's one more place I want to go.
I'm eating...
OK.
I never knew life could be so good!
It's OK. I don't think
he's dangerous... for the moment.
This is another fine mess you got yourself into.
I gotta find Cassie.
She's not here, mate. Run away again.
What?
Well, I've gotta tell her something.
Do you understand me?
I've gotta find her. I...
I love her.
Oh...
well.
Then we'd better attend to that need
with due dispatch, my friend.
Tony, you're my best friend,
but I really don't know what the fuck
you're on about most of the time.
Do you think that matters?
Sidney, I think, on balance, it helps.
I reckon Anwar's party, yeah?
Yeah. That's it! Let's go, for fuck's sake!
Tone, this is my dad's car.
Yep. I went round to get your clothes.
Your dad was watching the football
and I reckoned we'd get here
a lot faster if I nicked it.
You stole my dad's car again?!
Yeah, but I've got Effy to worry about now.
I'm meant to keep an eye on her
now she's a drug fiend.
Better get changed, mate.
You don't get the girl wearing Bermuda shorts.
Fuck it. Drive!
A mission of love... Cool!
God. You're like... totally...
...totally... fit.
I know.
I'm so sorry.
There's somebody just has to meet you.
PHONE RINGS
- Hi.
- 'Where are you, man?'
I'm outside, An. It's really fucking cold.
- 'Come inside.'
- I don't think so.
'Just come inside, man.
You gotta see this...'
No, Anwar.
It doesn't matter. I'm going, OK?
'Maxxie... Maxxie, I'm coming.'
Please.
Maxxie!
Hi, Mr Kharral.
You're just in time for the food.
- Dad, Maxxie's gay.
- We've got a fantastic lamb bhuna.
- My wife made it because she knows...
- Dad. Did you hear me?
And the spices are just so hot, you know.
Not too much, not too little...
I'm gay, Mr Kharral.
I always have been.
It's a fucking stupid, messed-up world.
I've got my God. He speaks to me every day.
Some things I just can't work out.
So I leave them be. OK?
Even if I think they're wrong.
Because I know one day
he'll make me understand.
I've got that trust.
It's called belief.
I'm a lucky man. Right?
Yes, Dad.
Come, Maxxie. The food's ready.
Jesus, Anwar! Who's the DJ?
That's Starship. Even I think that's wank!
- Can't be that bad. They've got lamb bhuna.
- What? Your mum's?
Yup.
Let's go.
- I've had the best birthday present ever.
- Cos you're back with your best mate, yeah?
No, stupid. I've pulled.
MUSIC BOOMS INSIDE
You coming in?
Go find Cassie.
Cheers, Tone.
Sid...
That was on your bed.
All right.
I'll see you.
Just you and me, sis.
Fucking wanker. >
Eff? What you talking about?
Michelle.
I tried.
Nah. Wanker.
- I said sorry.
- Wanker.
Effy!
I liked it better when you didn't talk.
Wanker.
Stay here.
VOMITING >
Hey, Cassie.
- Wow! Hi, Tony.
- Is she all right?
She couldn't make it stick.
Bummer.
I'm leaving tonight.
We're going to Scotland.
Sid's looking for you.
Tell him goodbye for me.
Tell him yourself.
No.
See you, Tony.
No, wait!
I've got you a going-away present.
I think you want to see this.
Style-wise it could be improved. But it made
several compelling thematic points.
MUSIC BLARES
MUSIC DROWNS SPEECH
MUSIC STOPS, CHEERING
Excuse me.
Give it back, mate.
Huh?
My ring's gone walkabout, cobber,
and I've come over all shonky.
I've heard that can happen.
You looking for a touch of this?
Oh, Merve,
we hardly know each other.
You don't want me and my Joeys
to spit the dummy.
Because they'll take you lower
than a dead dingo's donger.
Right. Now they've lost me.
Stop it! Stop it, all of you, for fuck's sake!
Give it back, Chris. OK?
Give what back?
All right.
Sorry.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have a happy event!
A very happy event! Everyone, whoo!
APPLAUSE AND CHEERING
No. No, it's not that. Listen!
MUSIC STARTS
It's yours, Angie. Do you want it?
...Throwin' our love away
And breaking every vow
Your love grows colder...
No.
Yeah. She loves me.
- Oh, my God!
- Oh, no!
Watch out!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Has anybody seen Cassie?
(Anwar's mum) Someone call the police!
(Anwar's mum) Not the face!
...I never dreamed you'd hurt me this way
What would your heart say
If it could just see you now?
Throwin' our love away
And breakin' every vow
Your love grows colder...
TINKLING RINGTONE
Hello, Tony.
'Michelle?'
What?
Michelle, I want to talk to you.
'I can't hear you.'
Michelle, listen... Is it a bad signal?
Hang on.
- Can you hear me now?
- 'Tony?'
I need to tell you something.
I'm a twat.
I don't know why I'm like this.
Maybe I can change.
'I can change.'
You're the only one.
'The truth is...'
The truth is, I love you.
HORN BLARES
BRAKES SCREECH
Tony! Ahhhhh!
Tony?
Tony!
Fuck!
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la
Now that I've lost everything to you
You say you wanna start something new
And it's breaking my heart you're leaving
Baby, I'm grieving
But if you wanna leave, take good care
Hope you have a lot of nice things to wear
But then a lot of nice things
turn bad out there
Ooh, baby, baby, it's a wild world
It's hard to get by just upon a smile
I'll always remember you like a child, girl
You know I've seen
a lot of what the world can do
And it's breaking my heart in two
Cos I never wanna see you sad, girl
Don't be a bad girl
But if you wanna leave, take good care
Hope you make a lot of nice friends out there
But just remember
there's a lot of bad and beware
Ooh, baby, baby, it's a wild world
It's hard to get by just upon a smile
I'll always remember you like a child, girl
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la
La
Baby, I love you
But if you wanna leave, take good care
I hope you make a lot
of nice friends out there
But just remember
there's a lot of bad and beware
Ooh, baby, baby, it's a wild world
It's hard to get by just upon a smile
And I'll always remember you like a child, girl
Ooh, baby, baby, it's a wild world
It's hard to get by just upon a smile
And I'll always remember you like a child, girl.
(Cassie) Hi.
(Sid) Hi.