Ladies and gentlemen, the seatbelt
light has been switched off.
You are now free to
move around the cabin.
We've reached cruising altitude
and are flying over the French Alps.
Sorry, man.
It's nothing to do with you!
It's the vibrations, innit?
Mm, yeah.
Fuck off, homo.
- You gonna be this horny the whole trip?
- Just wait till we get there. Oh, man.
Those Russian peasant babes will do
anything for some Levi's and a Big Mac!
Ok, everyone. Listen up.
Right, I want you all to remember
that this is not a holiday, ok?
This is your chance to nail your
module one history coursework...
post-Soviet industrial Russia.
It's a chance of a lifetime, gang.
Whoopee
Now, this isn't just education,
yeah? It's total education.
Total piss up.
Uh, no, no, no, no.
There'll be no "piss up", ok?
We're gonna work hard,
understanding the culture and history
of Mokshovkov in the Mordovian
Republic of the Russian Federation.
Ok? We're gonna see
the real Russia, yeah?
The wild and desolate land that
Napoleon and Hitler failed to tame.
This is adventure, yeah? This
is living, breathing history.
Who's with me?
Thank you, sir. I was
addressing history students only.
- This trip will blow their minds, and yours.
- Great.
Oi, An, An. Where'd you
hide the drugs, then?
- I thought you were bringing them.
- No. You were gonna put 'em in your turban.
I don't wear a turban, Chris.
I thought you were
gonna get one especially!
Don't panic, boys.
We've got a back-up plan.
Urgh, not up his arse?
Christ.
Jeez.
Thanks.
What's happening?
They think he's a fucking terrorist?
- Where they gonna take me?
- Do something.
- Right, ok. Leave it to me.
- Tom, maybe I should...
No, no, no. I'm trip leader.
If anyone's gonna be anally
searched, it should be me.
Trip leader. Let me through.
Nyet!
Get the fuck off me!
No, sorry, sorry. Listen,
listen! That boy is in my charge
and I can give you my
personal guarantee that...
Ah.
Oh, I see. Ok.
No, no, no. I've given you everything.
Ahh! There's nothing fucking up there!
No... ok, ok, ok.
That's totally stereotyping. You
gonna let them get away with it?
Now what?
Just walk on.
I'm trying
- they just look so disappointed I'm not a terrorist.
Well, you're a very dull
Muslim, Anwar. Very dull indeed.
ROAR OF AIRPLANE ENGINES
Excuse me.
Uh, hello, excuse me.
Hello, hi. Uh, we're
looking for our bus.
Um, we had an arrangement, uh,
for a bus to, uh, Mokshokov.
- Mokshokov?
- Um... How can I put this? Um...
- We ordered a bus.
- Ahh!
Ugh. Bet you never thought you'd
be doing this last week, eh?
No.
Fucking hell. This place better be good.
My hair is destroyed. I need a
shower and a decent hairdryer.
Oh, great, Tom. We're
staying in a fucking prison.
Don't judge a book by its cover.
This trip is all about
understanding other people's culture.
Hello!
Dobry den.
- Ya, Tom Barkley. And you are...
- Irene Kovskaya. Translator.
Come! I lock you in!
Ok, it's two to a room.
So pair up, people!
Raas! Russia's big, bruv!
Me's gonna be hyped up.
No, it's same sex only, I'm afraid.
So rearrange yourselves, yep.
Spoilsport.
Come, come.
- And we are going to be roomies, I'm afraid.
- What?
Yeah. Budget couldn't stretch
to single lodgings so...
We'll make ourselves comfy, yeah?
Yeah?
I pushed and pushed but still nothing.
What the fuck are we gonna do
here without any drugs? Look it it.
Don't blame me if
I've got guts of steel.
Dunno why you came anyway.
You don't even do history.
I thought it would be uplifting.
Let me have a go.
Cheers, man.
Magic fingers.
What the fuck?
What?
"Bad mood-comfy jim jams"?
What? You try arguing with a
45-year-old Pakistani woman, then.
Did she pack you these as well?
No, but she packed me this.
Seriously impressive, man.
- Must have taken ages.
- You can have it, if you want.
Cheers.
Dinner.
Wank or tell group?
Ah, tell group!
Guys, guys!
I've seen boobs! A girl with boobs!
God, that's pathetic, Anwar.
No. You wanna see this, though!
She's got a big chopper as well.
Oh, my God!
I wanna see that.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Guys,
guys, what about your dinner?
You don't wanna look at
the girl with the boobs?
Nah. I prefer Welsh women.
She was there a second
ago. She was there.
She'll come back. She
was just there, I promise!
Tell us when the Spice
Girls turn up, too, yeah?
Piss off.
She was there. She had boobs.
Yeah, whatever, man.
What you doing?
Looking for your "Sexy Saturday
Night Leopard Skin Thong."
We're going out on the pull.
- Make sure you don't bring anyone back.
- Huh?
We are sharing a room Max, yeah.
I don't wanna have to
pretend to be asleep
while you're doing whatever you
do with some big Cossack guy.
Maybe you can tempt your
big-boobed peasant girl in here.
Have a bit of party, you know?
Seriously, I don't wanna have to be
stuck around watching you do a guy.
Can I bring a girl back?
I could, couldn't I? You're shit, Anwar!
Have you ever tried being with a girl?
- What the fuck is wrong with you?
- Well, have you?
Well, have you ever
tried being with a man?
No! Don't be sick.
You calling me sick?
No!
I dunno what I think, yeah.
I'm just a Muslim.
Gay's... just wrong.
Then you don't want
anything to do with me.
- All right, Max?
- No.
Why?
Well, Anwar's decided
to become a Muslim.
What, like, more Muslim
than he was already?
A bit more Muslim, yeah.
Oh.
So I need to sleep in here, ok?
Fine. Sid'll swap. You
don't mind, do you, mate?
No, it's cool.
Maybe take your bag, too?
Thanks.
What happened?
He's just, like, switched
about me being... You know.
Blond?
- No!
- Short?
Gay!
Shall I give you head?
- What?
- It'll cheer you up.
For fuck's sake.
You're supposed to be a friend,
and I've come here with a problem.
- You fuck!
- We're in Russia. I wanna try something new!
I'm not a hobby, Tony. You're
not taking up canoeing here!
I've been canoeing.
- Well, what about Michelle?
- Loves canoeing.
- Tony!
- Fine.
What you doing?
I'm gonna get an early
night. Coming to bed?
Hey, Max. Can you give me and
Tony some time alone, please?
No. Yeah, Sure. Sorry.
Don't come in, Tom.
It's Chris.
Chris.
I'm changing. You ok?
Can't sleep.
Well, have you got a book?
Why would I have a book?
You're a student.
But we don't need books for
your sort of thing, do ya?
Psychology. It's all
in your head, innit!
Let me in and I'll show
you my reverse-psychology.
No.
Fine. I'll go away then.
All right.
Very clever.
So what do you want?
Just wanted to see you.
Ok.
And, er, maybe a goodnight kiss.
Hope you're decent!
Wait a minute!
Ok. Come on in.
Tom. You're staring.
Was I?
- Tom!
- Sorry.
Well, I'll be over there.
If you need me.
You ok?
Yes, um...
I'm sweet as a nut.
I bet you are.
Tom, what are you doing?
Squat thrusts.
97,96
95, 94, 93, 92,
91, 90...
Oh, my God.
Sid! Quick!
Still nothing...
She's back! In a bra and pants!
What? Pretend Spice?
You know sometimes, people
wanna see something so badly
they actually start to imagine
they have seen something?
Wakey-wakey!
Hour for cleansing.
Girls first clean, then boys clean!
There is no fucking way I am doing that!
All right, Max? Man, Sid's
farting last night was rough.
Just take it back.
Take back what you said.
See you.
Shit!
It's an experience. Come on.
Come on.
Where's your shampoo?
Much water for your dirty face.
It doesn't bloody wash off!
Okey-dokey, karaoke. Folks, listen up.
Listen up!
This way, please.
Now, there's been a few problems.
But are we gonna let it get us down?
No. So.
Let the education begin.
Horse come in.
We break legs.
Then crush.
Add water.
Boil, then glue.
Raas! My Little Pony get whacked
up big-time. Na wha' I'm sayin!?
Tom.
Yeah, all right. All right. Like I said.
This is the real world,
yeah? Real things happen.
Deal with it. Come on.
That's absolute crap, Tom.
I thought on this
trip, we could explore.
You know...
Explore each other?
Tom...
Fuck off!
Come on. Why do you think
I brought you on this trip?
You're totally, totally out of order.
Oh, yeah, and maybe you are frigid.
- Yeah?
- Mmm.
Well, fuck you, Tom!
Yeah.
Jesus Christ! What are you doing?
He can't talk to you like that.
- I'm gonna get the fucking twat.
- It's fine. It's fine!
What am I doing?
Come on... why not?
It won't take long.
- I'll be good, I promise.
- No.
Why? You've done everyone
else. Georgie, Chris, Sid.
How do you know?
I've seen. I heard about the
one with Kenneth and his mum.
Now, draw me.
Just stop it.
Stop it!
Come on, man, I'm inspirational.
Just stop it, yeah?
You're a fucking idiot. Look...
You've got a best friend who
thinks you're a perv, yeah,
and you drew him, but you won't do me?
I'll give you head... that's friendship.
The packet says that these tablets will
totally flush you out within 24 hours,
cos believe me, Sid,
we need those drugs.
- There's no drugs, Muslim boy!
- Cheers, Max.
You fucking prick. I can't believe
you're putting that Muslim bullshit on me!
- What?
- I'm against God?
You're the fucking worst Muslim!
- I pray five times a day.
- For what?
More pork chops? Fuck
it. Let's get a drink.
Of course Allah wants you
doing Class As from Sid's arse!
You're talking about my religion!
How was I ever friends
with a fucking hypocrite?
Happy fucking Ramadan.
It's not Ramadan!
Hey!
Whoa, easy man!
What fucking else?
My house! No break, no break!
I'm sorry... Sorry.
Ok.
- Neil Diamond?
- Yeah.
Neil Diamond!
Come.
So why are you with Tony?
He's exciting. And he must love me,
cos he could have anyone he wants.
Do you think he ever wants anyone else?
Maybe sometimes. He
always wants me the most.
I'm his girlfriend and
that's special, isn't it?
Yeah. I suppose. Listen, I
need to talk to you about him.
Look, I know I annoy you, Jal.
I don't mean to.
Can we get out of here,
please? Just you and me?
Sure.
Shit.
Sid. Sid!
Her dad's turned up and he's shouting.
It's like abuse, man.
Oh, so there's a dad now, is there?
Fuck.
- Fuck me. She's real.
- He's gonna hurt her. We've gotta help!
What are we gonna do?
- An, he's going. Her dad's going.
- Come on!
- Where are you going?
- Nowhere. Where are you going?
Nowhere.
- You sure you're not going anywhere?
- Yep.
Guys?
- You going somewhere?
- No!
Bye, then.
Neil Diamond.
Sit down, sit down!
What is problem?
You won't understand. I mean,
you can't even speak English.
No problem!
Vodka!
Now, you tell me problem.
We drink and problem kaput, da?
Ok.
Na zdoroviye!
I'm careering
Down that slippery slope
Cos the thought of you won't go away...
Chris, this... was a one-off.
I don't have sex with
my 17-year-old students.
How old are they normally?
What are we gonna do about Maxxie?
- You should hear what he gets up to.
- I'm serious, Chris!
Ok, I'll have a word.
And you do know that this can never,
ever happen again, don't you?
Yeah.
Ok. So the plan is?
We get in, rescue her, get out.
Sid's a big hero. Anwar
gets his marbles gargled.
Simple.
Hello!
Helloski!
Hey!
Hello!
Anka!
Sshhhh!
We're gonna get you out of here.
Sid.
Shhh!
Tie this to the bed. Hurry up,
he's gonna come back. Come on.
Come on, come on, slowly.
Go.
No, no.
Trust me, yeah. Go.
He's gonna get you, go.
Come on, come on.
Trust me.
Sid, keep watch!
Agh!
Anka.
Every time. Every fucking time.
"Buy two ounces of weed,
Sidney." "Oh, yes, sir!"
"Shove a bag of pills up your
arse, Sidney." "Oh, right away!"
"Come help me save some
random bint." "Oh, could I?"
What have we learnt, Sidney?
Your friends are shitheads.
Ahhhhhhh!
Great.
Ummm...
me...
name...
Anwar.
Me... name... Anka.
If only you knew the things
I'd love to do to you.
Rub my fingers through your hair.
Kiss your lips.
Kiss your neck.
Come on your tits.
Sounds like fun.
- You speak English?!
- Ya hah!
I learnt from, like, so
the best American show ever.
How you doin'?
I'm like... horny.
Come on, this'll do.
This is awful. Let's go.
J, I've never left a bar without
being chatted up in my life.
Not about to break that record now.
- There's nobody in here!
- If you flaunt it, they'll come.
Unbelievable.
Flaunt it, J.
Can you be any harder?!
Nope.
Friends?
Friends!
Anwar's a fucking liar. Lies
to his mum all the fucking time.
No, no, no, fuck that.
He makes me lie for him.
Who's Anwar?
Friend.
Who's homo?
Me! Anwar hates me
cos I'm a fucking homo.
Anwar hate homo?
Yeah.
Anwar is friend?
So, Anwar has problem. No,
Maxxie. Valentina help Maxxie?
Yeah, yeah, thank you.
Maxxie help Valentina?
Of course.
You want me to draw you?
Ok.
Urgh.
Kalinka, malinka, kalinka maya
Kalinka, malinka, malinka maya
Kalinka, malinka, malinka mayal
Three condomski down, 19 to go.
- Did you draw this?
- No.
He did.
He must be a good friend.
He'll be there for you when
the rain starts to fall.
Maybe not. He's pretty angry with me.
Why?
Cos I told the truth.
And that's important.
But what about you? You've
got bigger problems than me.
Anka, you can't go home back to him.
You should come home with
me. I'll look after you.
Anwar, don't lie to
me, it's not possible.
It is! Just, look...
We can live together in my
house. I'll look after you.
There may be one or two little
hiccups with the parents,
but I'm sure it'll be fine.
Guys! Guys! Sporty Spice
has finally arrived.
Anwar's in there with
a bloody Russian girl!
Tony, man, shhh!
What? Don't act like you
don't want everyone to see.
She's fit, though, ain't she?
Yo, yo, homies, what's happenin'?
- Yeah, she is fit. You must have paid for her.
- Yeah, Anwar, you pimp.
- Aye, what's poppin', baby love?
- Oi!
Perhaps she wants a
taste of the Kenneth.
Right, not to be boring
old teacher, yeah.
I mean, it's all gravy
with me, you know, but...
Sid!
You'd not believe what
I've just been through.
I jumped out of a window,
got chased into a bush,
waded through a river,
all the while being chased
by your nutter of a dad.
But it's ok, though,
cos I reckon I lost him.
Eurgh. Why's she kissing her dad?
- Anka?
- He's my husband.
Your husband?
We were on a break.
I'm sorry! I didn't know!
Leave him alone. Leave him alone.
Oh, my giddy aunt! Can
we be sensible about this?
Stop it, now! That's
enough, Maxxie. Now.
Can we talk? Can we talk?
Nyet!!
- Honestly, we leave you alone two hours.
- And look what happens.
Um...
He totally, like, wants to
know who is the leader here.
Yes, yes, officer, yes. Um, officer...
I wanted to thank you, er...
because before you arrived
I was about to step
in and kick some arse.
There is a charge for armed response.
Wh... what?
It's, like, you so totally
will have to pay them.
You English big hooligan problem.
Tomorrow you leave Russia.
Hey. You ok?
Man... you tried to save me.
Yeah. Well, I am fucking drunk.
You were right, Max.
I am a hypocrite.
- Go on.
- No. I can't.
It's not right.
It's religion, Anwar. It's just stuff.
You don't have to believe in it.
Then where does that leave me, Max?
I'm a Muslim boy.
I don't get to choose.
But where does that leave us?
Fucking hell.
I lost my virginity tonight.
Yeah?
Let's get us an old fat lady.
Last drop?
Ok.
I'll see you, mate.
- Hey, it's
He-Man. - Shut up.
Poor girl's totally out of
it. She's completely wasted.
Tony, you've got to stop fucking around.
I dare you.
Tony.
We've finally found
something you're not good at.
What?
Good night, Tony.
I'll find somewhere else to sleep.
What?
Oh, God.
Problem?
Tom, just shut up.
Hey, Cassie. That's good.
Ta.
She really looks...
- You made her look beautiful.
- She is beautiful.
- Tony.
- Yes, Nips?
Have you got something to tell me?
Er... I dunno.
I like your hair.
No. Your top's nice.
I love you? Any of those?
No.
Ahh. Oh, hang on.
I think it's...
I think I'm about to deliver!
Great. Just in time
for Heathrow security.
- Huh?
- Yeah. I hear they're very strict.
- Better keep it up there.
- Oh, God.
Oh, God.
corrected by chamallow35
www.addic7ed.com