Whoa... Chris.
It's not true, is it?
What?
They're all the same
size at action stations.
No...
Poor Chris.
Wow.
That's better...
Cool.
< Sami Allahu liman hamidah.
Rabbana wa lakal hamd.
Allahu Akbar.
Sami Allahu liman hamidah.
Rabbana wa lakal hamd.
Allahu Akbar.
< Rabbana wa lakal hamd.
Anwar?
Yup.
What date is it?
13th. What's up?
Allahu Akbar.
I think Michelle's
parents are back today.
Bummer.
Do you think I should remind her?
I'm trying to pray
to my god here, Cass.
Oh... wow...
Is he listening?
I hope not.
Otherwise he knows about all
those pills I necked last night.
Sing quietly.
Yup...
Allahu Akbar.
Cute.
Chelle...
Fuck off, Tone.
It's me, Cass.
Crazy bitch.
Yes.
Never fucking eats.
Right, but... Michelle...
Your mum gets back today... yeah?
Tomorrow.
Today's the 13th. Isn't it?
Mmm. Tomorrow.
Oh, hello, Cassandra...
Hi, Anna!
Hello, um...
It's Malcolm.
Malcolm, yeah, wow.
How was the honeymoon?
It was just wonderful, wasn't it babe?
Just us and 47 Namibian nomads
out there in the desert... Heaven.
Cool.
We do love a nomad, don't we, babe!
So have you been
helping Michelle clear up?
Oh, wow, totally.
I expect she told you about my
important meeting today?
Clients coming to look at
my curtain designs.
Right, can we get in?
I want some fucking Coco Pops.
Well, lovely to see you again Cassandra.
You're looking much better than
the last time I saw you. Well done.
Oh... You too.
Nice to meet you again, Martin.
It's Malcolm...
It's Malcolm.
For fuck's sake!
What's she on, hunger
strike or something?
Sshh!
Michelle, darling, here we are,
safe and sound.
Ahhhhh! What the fuck!
Mum! You didn't tell me!
Go go go... Come on, Jal...
Help...
Go!
I forgot my T-shirt.
GIGGLING
Ah! Oh, oh...
I want to eat you, fuck bunny.
Oh... Oh... Oh!
Whoaa!
Cassie...
How you doing, kiddums?
You had some breakfast?
Oh, yeah. Michelle's does crazy
bacon, egg and sausage sandwiches.
They're mad.
There! Great!
I'm going... for a shower.
Little wittle!!
Do you want me to... feed Reuben?
Oh, would you, sweetie?
I've got so much I've got to do...
< Hey!
Little wittle.
< Margie...
Thanks, poppet...
It's my final clinic day.
They'll sign me off if
I've gained a half kilo.
Oh, yeah? Have you done it?
Totally... For sure.
Hey... Hurray!
< I can't find the... uh... stuff!
< Coming!
Little wittle,
wittle, wittle, yeah.
OK. Yes.
All changed and clean, yes.
Little wittle,
look what we got for you. Look.
Greedy boy... Greedy boy.
MUFFLED GROANING AND BUMPING
< Oh, right!! Right!!
< Right a bit...
< Bit more...
MOBILE PLAYS GENTLE TUNE
RHYTHMIC BUMPING
AND MUFFLED SHRIEKING
TEXT ALERT BEEPS
GROANING AND BUMPING CONTINUE
MUFFLED SIGHING
Hey...
Kiddums! Oh, cheerful!
Thanks. I feel great, Dad.
Course you do... What do you think?
Oh, wow!
Amazing.
Cool.
Did Reubens do his poo?
Oh, Yes.
He's like all changed and asleep.
Ah, thanks, that's super!
The taxi's here.
Taxi?
They send it from the clinic
to make sure I go.
Yes, of course.
They're signing her off, darling!
Fantastic!
We knew you'd make it through.
Wonderful!
And don't forget to say thank you.
Oh... I will... totally.
Purple. I'm thinking, purple...
Yes...
Ah yes... Yes.
OK, my beautiful.
Show... me...
the money...
You got enough room
back there, Cassie?
You wouldn't tell on me,
would you, Alan?
You know me, kid. See no.
Hear no. Speak no.
They'll sign me out
if I'm half a kilo up.
Do you know what you're doing?
Oh, totally... I'm so fine...
I'll miss you, Tiny...
Oh, wow...
Yeah...
You too, Alan.
You gonna eat this time, Cassie?
Totally.
Hey.
Don't give me the smile.
Not that smile, OK?
OK, Alan.
Love you.
I love you too, Tiny...
Change of music?
Sure.
It's my new favourite.
We're in heaven
but we're living in hell
They think we're in heaven
When will they love,
only time will tell
They think we're in heaven
but we're living in hell
(RAPS) Whoever said life's easy,
well you're wrong
Where I'm from so much is going on
Every day the same bullshit,
it's more stress
It feels like I'm living
in the wild, Wild West
Depending on the beast
where the streets is curbed
If heaven is up there,
this is hell on earth
This is my society, sex, money and drugs
So I pay in the streets,
I'm like, where is the love?
Was it lost somewhere,
nowhere to be found
While money keeps making
the world go round.
I'm surrounded by bloodshed, yeah
More money, more problems -
that's what, big stuff
We need to make a change
but it will never stop
They think we're in heaven
but we're living in hell...
Can I see your pockets?
880 grams each.
Neat.
That's over
one-and-a-half kilos, right?
1,760.
Sorted.
I need to be quick.
Christ, I wanna wizz.
Busy... Wait, please.
Oh, fuck!
Get out off the fucking toilet!
Weight is correct.
"Demeanour...
Satisfactory.
"Attendance, Interaction,
Compliance... Yes, yes, yes.
"Mood... yes..."
How's your mood?
Oh... Fantastic. Really.
Excellent!
PHONE RINGS
Yes?
No... No...
I don't care who's going, Abigail.
You failed to comply with my wishes
regarding parties
and carpets were damaged.
Stop crying!
I am not an "expletive" bitch.
I am your mother!
Have you taken your medication?
Well, take it now...
Now!
So...
before you leave us
to start your new life,
it's important that you understand, um...
- Cassie.
- Cassie!
That if you are troubled again,
then you treat us
as a place of safety and refuge.
We like to think of Restoration
as a big family you can re-visit
any time it's necessary.
Here's my card with
the emergency number...
Calls after six are double.
We're all on your side.
Providing you have arrangements
in place for the fees.
How does that sound?
Lovely. I'm so grateful, really.
Good.
Thank you, Carrie.
You may go to Group Congratulations.
Dr Stock.
Thank you so much.
APPLAUSE
Well done, Cassie.
We'll miss you. Won't we?
Wow. Thanks everyone.
Right... Who's next?
Madison.
Can we congratulate you?
No, I'm not happy.
You!
You're staring at me.
No-one's staring at you, Madison.
Are we?
(Group) No... No...
Now. What's been troubling you?
I keep telling myself that maybe
I'm a bit over-sensitive, you know,
and it's... It's starting to work.
There's no more...
no more voices going,
"Ba ba ba ba ba,"
no more voices whispering,
you know, "Ba-ba..."
And then... And then...
Spit it out Madison.
We're here for you, aren't we?
(Group) We are...
Perfectly straightforward
business deal, right?
This kid asks me for credit terms
and I'm like...
"trust"...
Yeah?
Well done, Madison.
The only thing that I ask...
is repayment...
in a clearly defined schedule.
So I give him what he wants.
What did he want?
Goods and services...
This fat fuck.
This deceiving, scheming
little pluke!
He thinks...
that he can get away
with cheating me out of my money...
Maybe he wasn't trying
to cheat you, Madison.
Oh, yeah?
It's a misunderstanding.
Really?
We need you to work on this,
Madison.
Well, I'm working on it!
I'm working on it.
Er, chips, please.
Few more.
Just a few more.
Cheers!
Hi, Marnie.
What are we?
Pilchard.
Cute. What we saying?
We're saying we're an oily fish,
tasty and rich in healthy
life-giving Omega fats.
Sodding Jamie Oliver.
Bummer.
Go on, then.
You sure?
Yes, why not, I'm into long life.
Cheers, Marnie.
See you later.
Smart-arsed blonde fucker.
All right.
- All right, Sidie boy.
- Kiss me, you fool!
Yeah, white boy!! Wha gwan. Rrraas!
You get me!?
Dis blood him lubed up, man!
White boy got bear shit
on him forehead and ting!
What's the frequency, Kenneth?
Sorry.
Got a bit carried away there.
I think you did, man.
Oh, do stop it, OK?
It's not funny.
Can I sit here?
Yeah, sure, go for it.
Oh, cool. So nice of you.
You been home, Sid?
No, came straight from Michelle's.
You left before her mum
called the police?
Yeah.
Went a bit wrong.
Then Tony had to go and Jujitsu
Mr Michelle's cos...
Well, because he's a total
fucking wanker really.
You love Tony.
Pardon?
I said, you love Tony.
You always talk about him.
Do I?
I mean, it's cool you've
got someone to look up to.
Oh, it was fun.
Throwing all that food around.
Just like, throwing it everywhere.
Wow. Wow!
Whoa.
You must be hungry.
Yeah. Bit of a hangover and... Yeah.
There.
Go on then.
You gonna eat that?
Oh, totally.
I'm better now. I'm totally better.
How do you do it?
What?
Come on, Cass.
I mean you never eat anything.
Your parents must notice
or something.
I dunno.
I like you, Sid.
OK.
So I'm going to show you.
You have to do a lot of talking.
I'm good at talking.
You do that while you're cutting
things up a lot. Then, questions.
Where's your Student Card?
Sorry?
Your ID, have you got it?
No I, er, lost it
somewhere last week.
Change the subject.
This is great.
I love these sausages.
You should try one. Go on.
Delicious. Mmmm.
Hang on you didn't...
You're not quite sure what I'm on
about but I keep distracting you.
Then I up the ante.
Yum. I love this stuff.
Really delicious.
You're reassured I want some more
and I'll keep waving it at you
until you stop looking at me.
Where did you lose it?
Sorry?
Your ID. I mean, they won't let
you use the library, will they?
God, I've gotta go.
Oh.
I'm so full.
Gotta dash.
There you go. Job done.
That's impressive.
Cheers.
But aren't you kind of, you know,
lying to everyone?
I'm so better.
I got discharged from the clinic.
Seems a bit fucked up.
What?
I said just seems a bit
fucked up, that's all.
Oh, wow.
But you see...
It's like nobody's fucking business.
And it's not exactly
like anybody cares, so...
I care.
Look. Pilchards. Cool.
And I got it from a fish lady.
Yeah, I wasn't so keen on them.
What you fucking talking about?
Omega fats and fishy oils,
they're cool.
I was just chatting to Cass, Tony.
Hey, Cass.
How's dippy world?
She's better. She just got
discharged from the clinic.
Yeah, whatever. Jesus!
What?
Don't you ever wash?
That's like lipstick.
Yeah, man, the essence of woman.
Well, one at least.
So who's the lucky lady?
That's like someone kissed me.
I can't believe you haven't
washed man. You stink!
Somebody kissed me.
Well, yeah, mate,
that's a total fucking operator
error cos you stink.
I didn't have time.
Time? I've been home, showered,
done my Chi, had a wank,
subtly undermined my dad,
put new clothes on and here I am
with my English coursework.
English coursework. Oh, fuck!
Sometimes I wonder why you even
bother to get up in the morning.
You're such a complete fucking
waste of time and... Ahh, shit!
Wow, Tony. Bummer. It looks
like you pissed yourself.
That's not supposed
to fucking happen.
Look at Tony, man. Ah, shit man!
Raas blood white boy gone
piss himself up you get me!
Mandem's sick stains. Hey, Cuz!
Yo got serious stains!
Him cream up his pussy good style.
I'm a bad person.
Come on!
< That hurt, actually!
Gotta go. Sure you have.
Finish off the rest of my
food if you want.
OK.
This guy from my group
therapy's got your ID card.
And he's a crazy fuck and he
hates you because you cheated him.
What's his name?
He likes to be called Mad.
Twatter.
Yeah. Totally. What did you do?
I bought some dope on the tick,
and then we lost it
in the harbour and...
Oh, fuck. Fuck.
Tony!
This is a room for female staff.
Yeah. The drier's broken in ours.
Ah, there you are.
Jesus, we're in trouble!
That crazy fucking dealer
found us, Tony. Hi, Angie.
We gotta do something. I mean, you
could talk to him and... Oh, fuck.
Oh, you wankers.
That was well funny, man.
But someone's gonna have to apologise
cos Kenneth's crying now so...
Oh, Jesus Christ,
Holy Mary, Mother of God!
That's Angie! Don't look! Get out!
For fuck's sake! Fuck off!
< Sorry, Angie.
You still got it.
Get out of there
and don't look at her, all right?
You like me. You like me.
Look up if you like me.
Oh, bugger.
Shit!
Oh! Sid.
Hi. Sorry, Angie.
You shouldn't go into
the staff showers, Sid.
I know, I know.
It was a crisis.
Well, it's just a bit
embarrassing that's all.
Actually, I'm pretty
confident about my body...
No, I'm having a crisis.
Oh.
Well, sometimes adult bodies can be
a little overwhelming.
Oh, for Christ's sake, Angie,
I don't care about your tits!
Oh.
I'm in deep, deep, deep shit.
Right.
OK.
You need advice?
I need advice and 300 quid.
Otherwise someone's going to
be re-possessing my bollocks.
OK, well look, when it comes to debt,
the best thing to do is to face up
to it before it gets out of hand.
Yeah?
Yeah. All you have to do is go
to the person you owe money to
and calmly ask them to
reschedule the payments.
Reschedule payments?
So that's one ball now
and then the balance next week.
Believe me, Sid,
I'm a responsible adult.
I know. OK?
Now what was it,
a phone or something?
Actually, Angie, it was three
ounces of prime hydroponic skunk.
Shit!
Yeah, shit.
Go to the police.
They'll arrest me.
Give it back.
I lost it in the harbour.
Keep your head down.
He's got my student ID card.
Right.
Right. OK.
Basically, I'm fucked, aren't I?
Yep.
Well, thanks, Angie,
I feel a lot better now, yeah.
Look, give me a moment. I'm sure
I can come up with something...
No, sorry.
Chris.
Mm-hm.
You've come to apologise, right?
Huh?
To say sorry.
Oh, yes. Erm, yes, I'm sorry.
Sorry I saw your boobs.
Sorry I saw your bum.
Erm, sorry I saw your...
Apology accepted, Chris.
Right.
Well, I've got work to do.
So if you're done...
Yeah.
Chris.
You shouldn't look at me like that.
Sorry.
It isn't appropriate.
I'm your teacher and...
Have you always had that mole?
Um... Yes.
It's lovely.
Oh, God.
PHONE BUZZES
OK, right, everybody, listen up.
I'm gonna be taking in
your assignments today.
Why are you so relaxed about this?
So he's got your ID Card.
So what?
Um... everybody?
So what? He's gonna cut
my fucking bollocks off!
Chill out, Sid. I'm chilled, right?
Why are you so chilled?
I'm confident and relaxed
with my ability to improvise.
I'm going on a course
for the rest of the week,
and I'm not going to be here.
Also, I didn't buy the drugs.
You did.
Nice one, thanks, Tone...
Guys, look... We've got a supply
teacher coming in for next week
and in fact, he's on his way up
from the office now to say hello.
Everybody...
Look. There's 3,000 students at
this college. He won't find you.
So if you give me your assignments,
I promise that I'll have them
marked for you by the...
Hi, can I help?
Supply teacher!
Oh, Hi. Hi. Hi. We really
appreciate the short notice.
Everybody this is Madison.
Madison...
...Twatter.
CHUCKLING
PhD.
Nice to meet you, Tom.
- You got a problem?
- No, no...
Because, er it's been a while
since I... taught...
I just... I just wanna say that it's
a beautiful, beautiful thing to do.
Right. Um...
Right, so you'll start next week?
No. No, I've already started.
I don't know,
checking lists and things.
Checking lists?
Yeah. Who's who and
what's what and blah blah.
I'm really looking forward to,
er, to meeting you.
Oh, I'm beside
myself with excitement.
I'm totally beside myself.
(Anwar) Sid.
Sid. Look at me, man.
Oh, God.
What's happening for Christ sakes?
His fucking dealer's
a supply teacher.
Oh, God.
So?
So he's gonna cut
Sid's bollocks off.
(Anwar) Sid.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Sid. Sid. I'm going to tap you, OK?
Oh, God.
Maybe a bit harder.
For Christ sakes!
Right. It's a problem but Sid's our friend and
we're going to solve it, OK?
Got that, Sid? We're gonna
put our heads together
and come up with a solution.
Sid. We're here for you. We're
thinking of the answer right now.
Anyway, I've got sociology so em...
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
Don't we have to go
over your French, yes?
Yeah, we should go.
Hang on.
We're going to give this some
serious thought, yeah, guys and... OK?
We can't just leave him like this.
We'll get back to him.
Yes, that's it. OK?
See you later, man.
We're gonna
get back to you on this, Sid. OK?
Mum?
This is Sid - your son.
Listen, I've got a problem.
Could you ring me back please?
BEEPING
Sid. Are you OK?
Bit fucked up as it goes.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Yeah.
It's like totally kind what you're doing, but it
won't make any difference.
Huh?
The texts you're sending.
The messages...
What are you on about, Cass?
I've got a few problems
here of my own, you know?
I know, but...
Thanks anyway, for trying.
Cassie, I haven't been
sending you any messages.
I just saw you.
There aren't any messages on here.
What?
There aren't any
messages on your phone, Cass.
I thought...
I thought you liked me.
What?
Nothing.
BABY CRIES
Hello.
Yes, it's Cassie.
I think I need to see you again.
Hi.
Hello, kid. What's up?
I'm having a few probs.
Oh, Cassie. I'm listening.
There's somebody I like.
I thought he was
sending me a message -
texts and things, but he wasn't.
What was the message?
"Eat."
Right.
It wasn't you, was it, Alan?
I don't tell you what to do,
Cassie. I'm just a taxi driver.
So, like,
who's telling me to eat?
Who wants you to eat?
You got permission.
I haven't got a knife and fork.
You don't need them.
No.
What kind of day did you have?
Fine.
Have you got any more good tunes?
I love you, Cass.
I love you, too, Alan.
So eat.