CHURCH BELLS RING
ALARM BEEPS
RADIO ON
BEEPING
THRASH METAL PLAYS
(Man) Tony!
Tony!
For Christ's sake, Tony!
- Sorry! The volume's bust again!
- Turn it down!
- I'm trying!
- Every fucking morning!
Why don't you just
get the sodding thing fixed?!
All right. All right.
- Pull the plug out!
- What?
Pull the fucking plug out, you twat!
Jesus Christ, Tony!
Pull the plug out, you pillock!
Tony!
MUSIC CONTINUES
Oh, shit!
MUSIC STOPS
DOOR HANDLE RATTLES
(Man) Bugger!
KNOCK AT DOOR
- How long you gonna be in there?
- Not long now.
Oh, fucking, bollocking, twat, fuck.
How come I'm never allowed to use
my own sodding bathroom?!
Oh, Jesus wept.
SPITS
Hey, sweetheart, do you want
some eggs?
No, thanks.
Effy's having some.
She didn't sleep too well.
(Man) Get out of the bathroom.
I need a piss!
Tony! He won't even answer me.
I mean, what's he doing up there?
Perming his fucking pubes or something?
Anthea, what is he doing?!
I think that lock's messed up again.
I put the drill under the sink.
You take me for a complete
James Blunt, don't you?
- Do you want an egg?
- I want a fucking piss.
Jim, I was wondering,
do you have to swear all the time?
Sodding, fucking, bollocky
shit, wank. Where is the twat?
DRILL WHIRS
(Jim) Every fucking morning!
RINGING
MOBILE BUZZES
Fuck off.
- Wake up, Sid, you twat.
- 'I'm asleep.'
No, you're not.
'Or just too bored to speak to you,
so leave a message.'
You're a lazy turd, Sid.
We have plans, remember?
Concerning your cock. Ring me.
RINGING
'Waaaagh! Got you! I'm not here,
you wankers. Leave a message.'
Jesus, dozy fuckers.
MOBILE RINGS
Tony? What?
- Jal, can you nip round and wake Sid up?
- Nip round? He lives half a mile away.
- Just nip round and quickly give him a...
- 'I'm trying to fucking practice here.'
'I've got another call. Stay on the line.'
Jesus.
Hi, Nips.
'Stop calling me, Nips.'
'It's a funny name.
'I've seen a few nipples, Nips,
and yours are fucking hilarious.'
My nipples are not funny, OK?
'That's your opinion. Anyway, you said
you'd help out with Sid today?'
What?!
With Sid. The virgin thing.
You weren't serious?
He's got to pop his cherry and I've
nominated you to, you know, help out.
God, Tony. Do I have to?
You promised. Hang on,
I've got Chris on the line. Stay there.
Whatever.
Yeah, man. You rang?
'Where the fuck is everyone?
It's nine o'clock.'
Oh man, I'm in bed.
Can't you go and get Sid?
I can't. I'm busy.
Busy-busy, you remember?
Ah, Buck Tooth?
Yo!
Give her a big hello from me, yeah?
You already did that, didn't ya.
It's my turn now. All right, laters.
Anyway,
it's not that much to ask, Nips.
Sid's almost 17. He's gotta get laid
before his birthday otherwise
he can't be my friend, obviously.
- What the fuck are you talking about?!
- Sorry, Jal. Wrong call. Can you hold?
- No.
- Perhaps you could help out with Sid's cherry.
'I don't think so! You need someone deaf,
blind and stupid for that.'
- That's unkind.
- Bye, Tony.
Wanna come to a party?
'Goodbye, Tony.
And stop calling Michelle Nips.'
It's a funny name.
She's got a funny nipple...
'You still there?'
- All right.
- 'Huh?'
I'll help Sid if he's so desperate.
'Safe. We'll do it at
the party tonight, yeah.
'Meet us in the cafe so we can plan.'
I have to plan?
- Oh, yes. Later, Nips.
- 'I said don't call me...!'
They're fine!
MOBILE RINGS
I can't talk right now. Ooow!
Cheers, Tony.
Tony?
- Hello, Mr Jenkins. It's Tony.
- 'Hi, Tony. What can we do for you?'
We're a little worried about Sid. He's got
a sociology test in ten minutes and, er...
'What? He's what?'
(Man) Wake up you lazy, bone-idle,
little fucker!
Ah.
Up! You complete and total fucking
sodding waste of fucking space!
What?
(Tony) 'Cafe now!
We've got things to talk about.'
Like what?
- Virgins.
- 'Huh?'
Virgins. Virginity.
Whose?
Yours, you anus.
- I'm listening.
- 'Hang on.'
Tony?
Cheers, Tone. My uncle wants
to stone me to death now.
- 'No, he doesn't. Your uncle's lovely.'
- What was it?
Party tonight.
Sid's getting de-cherried.
Chris promised Maxxie we're gonna
go to his big gay night out.
Is Chris gay?
- No.
- Are you gay?
No. But Maxxie says there's gonna be
lots of hot women there...
...desperate because there's nobody
to shag - except for me and Chris.
Anwar, you dippy twat. Sid's flying
solo down the tunnel of love
and he needs support, yeah?
Could we watch?
Oh, Jesus!
PHONE RINGS
Yup.
Hey, Maxxie. We need you tonight.
Sorry, Bruv. Big, gay night out.
Me and the lads.
The lads?
Yeah. I'm going to take them on
a voyage of wonder and discovery.
'Fuck that!
Look, Max - for Christ sakes!'
Can you stop fucking tap dancing?
I can't hear myself think.
Sorry, Tone. Gotta get these moves.
You know - for the show.
Do they have tap dancing
in Death Of A Salesman?
It needs a number.
I've always said that.
'Anyway, meet me on the green
before psychology.'
Got ya.
God, I'm good.
Sid.
Sid, you still there?
- Sid!
- Er, yeah?
A personal briefing is essential.
Cafe, 20 minutes.
'Tonight, Sidney my Cherry o' Baby,'
you present Mr Happy with
the keys to the Furry City.
Tonight, Mr Happy.
The Furry City.
BELCHES
I'm crap in the mornings.
You're always crap. No exercise,
rubbish food and too much caffeine.
Fuck off.
I didn't have a sociology test, did I?
No.
Fucker.
This better be good.
Trust me. Tonight we go to a party
and you finally pop the cherry.
You finally get the VIP tour
of Netherland. You finally...
Fuck off! "Finally".
It's embarrassing.
It's common and quite normal
for someone of 16 to...
No. It's embarrassing, Sid.
Shit.
All right. How?
We go to the party and we get a girl
catastrophically spliffed up.
In her confused state, she comes to
believe, however momentarily,
that you're attractive enough to shag.
- Who's the lucky girl, then?
- I think you're gonna like this.
Oh, yes. You are a very,
very lucky little boy.
Michelle?
I'm gonna do it with Michelle?
- Hang on, Sid.
- I'm gonna dock the ferry with Michelle.
Cheers, Tony. You don't know what...
Hi.
...what this means.
Are we getting me laid or shall I just start
filming and take it back for private time?
All right. Who's stupid enough
to fuck Sid?
Cassie.
She's still in hospital.
They let her out. She's just
not allowed to handle knives.
All right. She'll do.
We're gonna need a lot of drugs.
Get an ounce.
We can sell it at the party.
I've got to get an ounce of spliff?
There's this guy who'll sell on tick.
Tell him we'll pay tomorrow.
But why don't you go?
Got tai chi, then my choir audition,
then psychology.
Cassie's great in the sack.
As long as she's not hungry.
Who says?
(Both) Everyone.
OK, fuck it. What's this guy's name?
It's all on there.
That's this guy's name?
Mad Twatter?
Is that waking up your chi,
Karate Kid?
PIANO PLAYS
You've gone away
But I feel you near
The softness of your touch
is somehow always here
And I watch with my ever sorry eyes
Knowing I'm not discreet
when you leave me
You've far from me
And my guard is down
I wanna hear it said
they'll never part somehow
To just love me more
And I know for sure
That I'm just not discreet
when you leave me
And when I'm alone
I think how much I miss you
And long for the day
when you will miss me too
I sit on my own and dream of
how I'll kiss you
And you see me in the way that I see you
You're far away
Will be gone a while
I look into a sunbeam
Where I see you smile
And I have to go
Cos deep down I know
That I'm just not discreet
When you le-e-ave me.
That was lovely, Anthony.
Really, quite lovely.
Thanks.
I'm sure we'd love to have you
in the chamber choir.
Looking forward to it.
- Hi.
My frands think
you're really cool, yah?
- Your... sorry?
- My frands.
Are you still coming to my party
tonight? It'd be safe if you did.
Bring some frands.
My parents are in Cloisters.
We're just going to
go wild on drum'n'bass.
Sounds great.
After 8.30 because Miriam has to
get back from her cello recital.
- No problem.
- Bring some frands.
PHONE RINGS
I absolutely will.
Gotta dash. See you later.
Did you find Cassie?
She's coming, right?
Christ's sakes, Michelle!
Tell her we've got spliff and all
the Cheesy Wotsits she can eat.
I'm going to psychology. I'll come
and do you with the magic motor.
You got new batteries?
Nice. Warm it up for Super Fly.
You! You, boy.
What's your business in here?!
- Interview.
- I doubt that.
This is an all-girl school.
Where should you be, boy?
I'm at Roundview College.
And you think you can just walk in here
and accost ladies, do you?
I was auditioning
for the City Chamber Choir,
responding to a perceived need
for more male parts, man.
My name is Mr Griffiths and I'm the head
of French here and addressed as "Sir".
Do they even teach you French
in that technical college you attend?
They do.
And what do you call
your French teacher?
Pierre.
You! Come here! I want to
know your name. Come here!
I'm talking to you. I'll report you
to your college, you common oik!
Hey, it's me.
Yeah, did you find it?
I think so.
I dunno, Tone.
Totally fucking weird, OK?
'I don't care if it looks weird, Sid.
Get on with it!'
All right.
MOBILE PHONE RINGS
I told you, Tony. I'm fucking doing it.
Oh!
Are you my 2.30?
- 'Sid.'
- Hi, Mum.
- You here to see Alicia?
- I'll ring you back?
Come in, for Christ's sakes.
- 'Where are you?'
- College.
The neighbours
are bitching with the cameras.
I gotta go.
I'm not talking to anybody.
I've got to go.
Alicia?
I'm going to French.
I'll talk to you later.
Little geek guy here! Is he yours?
Hi.
You here for a threesome?
Big Issue?
- Get a fucking job, Kenny.
- Fuck you.
- How was the holiday?
- Shit. Faliraki's gone downhill.
Crap hotel. Four stars means
nothing now. Fucking nothing.
See ya.
Big Issue, love?
(Girl) Here he comes, cock of the year.
(Boy) So who's gonna tell him
we can't go to the party?
Shut up. Here he comes.
What you been doing in
Poshville Towers, eh?
Broadening my horizons.
Those girls do not do fickety fick
with town scum like you.
It doesn't matter what
you can do with your muscles.
I say this world extends way beyond this field
of dreams. And I want to see that world.
What the fuck's he on about?
He's quoting. It's a literary reference.
What? You mean Shakespeare and shit?
Dawson's Creek.
I don't know what that is, but if you guys
want to waste your life watching television...
- You don't watch television, Chris?
- No, I don't watch television, you braindeads.
Can you not think of anything better
to entertain yourselves?
Like?
Like pills.
Is that it?
No.
Shagging.
- Cultural.
- Oh, yeah.
It fucking is cultural.
You're full of shit. Nobody's gonna
shag you with a cock that tiny.
You shouldn't have got it out.
It was strip poker,
what do you want me to do?
You weren't even playing!
You shouldn't have got it out, Chris.
Just because you lot are such
a bunch of pussies.
Enough of that. Gotta go because we got
psychology. We don't want to miss Angie.
You will come to this party tonight?
- Aaah, I can't, man.
- (Girl) Me neither.
(Max) We told you! Big gay night out.
We'll have a shed-load of spliff.
Look, we don't need any.
The town's awash.
It's like someone planted up Lithuania.
Oh, Christ.
Sid's scoring an ounce now.
Call him off, man.
You'll be oversupplied.
Sid?
Answer, you twat!
HUMMING
You wish you could have me back
And be your fool forever...
I got to walk in on
'em by mistake now.
Do you want a coke or something?
No. Do you think he'll be long?
Not once I burst in all
flummoxed up, he won't.
No, I meant the guy I came to see.
Mad?
Mad. Is that... Is that his real name?
Oh, yeah.
RHYTHMIC BANGING ON WALL
You know what, I think
I'll come back later.
It's fine. Just don't stare.
He doesn't like people staring.
Right.
He's sensitive, you know.
Just don't stare at it.
At...
At what?
< Hello!
< I've unexpectedly
come home early by accident!
RHYTHMIC BANGING GETS FASTER
Sid, for Christ's sakes
don't buy the dope. Nobody's coming.
We're aborting the mission.
And Sid. Pick up your messages,
you absolute and utter lower colon!
SIGHS
RHYTHMIC BANGING AND MOANING
SCREAMING
Oh, fuck this.
You staring at me?
No, not at all.
So, er, you're Mad?
Yes, I am.
Maddison Twatter...
PhD.
You got a problem?
No, no, no.
Um, so you're a doctor, then?
Who said?
Well, the Ph... D thing.
Yeah, yeah, you could say that.
You could say, um, pretty... huge...
...dick.
LAUGHS MANICALLY
Yeah!
CONTINUES TO LAUGH
Which?
Doctor, Pretty Huge Dick. Which?
Both?
I like you. What's up, kid?
I mean, do you wanna...
Do you wanna get laid?
Huh? How did you?
I mean.
No, no. I was, er, looking
to maybe get some spliff.
LIGHTER CRACKLES
You being fucking funny?
Absolutely not.
Show me some money.
Right, well. That's the thing.
Cos someone said that maybe
I could get the stuff, and pay, like...
...later?
- Woah.
- Oh, fuck!
Credit terms. That's just a whole
fucking shark attack there, right?
I quite understand.
Let's just forget...
No, fuck it. It's your game,
if you want to play it.
Do you wanna play?
Yeah, yeah... Yeah.
Um, how about an ounce of spliff?
Three ounces it is.
No, no, an ounce... of... spliff.
Three ounces.
That's three hundred pounds
of easy credit,
so you've got 48 hours to pay me.
SOFA CREAKS, BAGS RUSTLE
Have you got balls?
Yeah.
I'm just checking, because
your balls are your collateral.
You got me?
Yeah.
After time, denial,
anger and bargaining will
give way to a depression.
In this phase the sense of emotional loss
is amplified and may seem unbearable.
WEEPING
In this phase, the feelings of low self-esteem
and hopelessness are common.
But these will finally give way, eventually,
to the final phase of acceptance...
WEEPING CONTINUES
...an understanding that what
has been lost can never return,
and that life can continue
although it may be very different.
(Sobbing) Oh, God!
SOBS
And a journey is complete.
No more sports science teachers, Angie.
SOBS SUBSIDE
I know.
- Hey, it doesn't matter how big his dick is...
- Shut it, Chris.
You're all so lovely to me.
I need you...
your coursework in by next week
for the deadline, if that's OK.
It's important for my department score,
you know...
SOBS
I could say that he touched me up
in the shower or something.
Could you?
- Chris, you idiot!
- What? What?
Where the fuck have you been?
Doing What you said. I fucking hope
this is still on. You got hold of Cass?
- Yeah, but thing is...
- Great. Well, I got the spliff.
Didn't you get my messages, you tit?
MOBILE PLAYS WELCOME CHORDS
MESSAGE BEEPS
MORE MESSAGE BEEPS
SIGHS
Problem?
MESSAGE BEEPS
Please!
You OK, Angie? Another day,
another dollar, eh?
Yes.
Can I carry your books?
Um, yes, but you don't
have to do it every day, Chris.
I do.
MOBILE RINGS
- I'll get it.
- No need...
Angie's phone... Stop ringing her,
or you'll have me to deal with.
- Let me have it.
- Yep, Chris Miles here.
Angie's friend.
She's got friends, you know
what I'm saying, you tosser.
Right. Yeah, yeah, I'll have
the coursework in by Thursday.
Are you saying
I can have an extension?
Yeah.
Don't ring her again... bell end!
Sorted him out!
Right.
I'm not sure you're supposed to...
Thanks, Chris.
Pleasure is all mine, Angie.
Shall we?
Jesus. Is that it?
Yup. It's Abigail's party. And we've
got to sell an ounce of dope.
I was meaning to talk to you...
So we tell them it's like,
Mongolian Hallucinogenic or something.
They're all so dim
they might just buy it.
- Yes, but you see, that's the thing.
- Tony!
- Hey.
Where is everyone?
Not coming. And Sid has to sell
or he's in shit with his dealer.
Hang on. "My dealer"?
Anyway, I brought Cassie.
Cassie, you remember Sid, right?
Yeah, wow, lovely... No.
But I like that you're funny-looking.
That's cute - like, wow, man.
- How's the treatment going, Cassie?
- Oh, it's cool.
I wear a white dress
and now I can eat yoghurt,
Cup-a-Soup and hazelnuts now.
I'm not sick if they let me
play with the cats.
Yeah, it's like...
...hazy days, you know.
Well, that's encouraging.
Oh, thank you. You're so nice.
Cass, Cass, Cass! Sid's going
to be looking after you tonight.
Oh, would you? Wow!
And Sid's got a whole bag of drugs.
Wow!
That's so nice.
And I bet you won't even
make me eat anything.
No. No.
Thank you.
Right, great! Let's go in
and shift this ounce, then, yeah?
It's three ounces.
I got three ounces.
Hi, Abi.
Tony! Lovely.
And these must be your frands.
Sorry?
Yeah, this is Michelle,
Cassie and Sid.
Super.
Wow, you're lovely.
Where's the kitchen?
I want to see the kitchen.
It's through there. Come in.
Cheers.
Oh... shoes.
It's just that Mummy had this carpet
imported from Iran.
We have to be so,
so careful with the pile.
Right, yep, sure.
Sorry.
(Tony) No problem.
Can I get you some rum punch?
I'm afraid we're getting rather
giggly on it - isn't that safe!
Mmm, we love rum punch,
don't we, Chelle?
Super.
Everyone, this is Tony and his frands.
Tony, this is Sarah, Josh, Sarah,
Maddie, Felicia, Hugo,
Sebastian, Sarah, Sam and Sarah.
- What was your name again?
- Sid.
Sid? Is that Polish or something?
No, I don't think so.
Danuta's Polish. Danuta.
She doesn't speak English.
But you can just speak to her
in Italian or in French.
She likes you.
Oh. Cheers.
Abi, I wonder if you and your friends
would like a little something?
Something?
You know, get a bit squiffy.
Oh, ya, that would
be so safe, you know.
Great, because we've got some
really cool shit which would get you...
- But we can't smoke anything in the hice.
- The "hice"?
Yes, because the silk wallpaper's just
arrived from Rome, and Mummy's particular
about odours, and we simply
mustn't, or she'll go wild.
Bummer.
OK, yah. This is MC Hugo on the decks,
and we're going to have
a tremendous time, yah?
(All) Yah!
So let's chizzle
on this dizzle and party down.
RAP MUSIC PLAYS
Isn't that something?
Ghetto-stylee.
Oh, come on, Tony!
Isn't this just bitching?
Come on, Tony.
JARS RATTLE AND CLUNK
Hi.
Oh, hi.
This is so, so wicked.
They've got such cool food.
Look at it all.
Wow.
Right. Are you hungry or something?
Oh, no. You mustn't eat it.
Just... arrange it.
They haven't got it organised
properly at all.
There.
That's it. Much better.
I don't feel sick now.
Cool.
So... are you going to fuck me later?
Pardon?
You know. Like Michelle said.
She said that?
Oh, yes.
Look, I've got all this fucking weed.
Do you want a spliff or something?
No.
I can't.
It makes you hungry.
- Well, I don't mind.
- I do.
Sorry.
Oh...
wow.
You can keep me company, yeah?
Yeah.
HOUSE MUSIC PLAYS
GENTLE MUSIC PLAYS
Jesus.
As big gay nights go...
It's not that big.
I'm sorry, guys. I just wanted
to show you my world, you know.
I'm definitely not turning gay.
Me neither. Nope.
It can be a lot of fun.
We had the Pontypool Mounted Police
Formation Dance Team in last week.
What a blast!
- Well, just have to imagine that.
- Hey, where you going?
To find that party.
- Nah.
- It's posh kids. All the boys are gay.
Yeah?
Are the girls gay too?
Look, everyone's gay. Right,
let's get the fuck out of here.
GIRL SHOUTS
I think we found it.
Bosh!
Double bosh!
And it only took five hours,
four buses and two bottles of vodka.
REGGAE MUSIC PLAYS
Man, check this thing out!
- Cool, man.
- Yeah!
Ooh, yep.
Careless.
Hey, Tony...
Tone. Changed our minds, man.
The monkey man's here!
PANTING
Wow!
Oh!
Wow.
This is lovely, lovely, lovely. Wow.
Waoo!
Cassie? You OK?
Get up here.
You've got to, got to bounce. Whoo!
(Abi) Tony, it's too wild, too wild.
Take them off, take them off!
OK.
I'm totally wired...
Fuck!
Oh, shit!
It's no good though, Sid. Is it?
What? What is?
You fancy me?
I... Sure, I...
But you really love Michelle.
It shows?
Fucking right it shows.
Anyway, she told me.
She told you?
Oh, fuck.
She said that Tony
doesn't love her properly, but you do,
and it's too fucked up because
she totally loves him even though
she thinks you're sweet.
Sweet? She thinks I'm sweet.
I'm in so much shit.
No, you're not.
No?
I mean, what would you do if...
if everything's so fucked up, and you...
and you just don't know what to do?
I stop eating until
they take me to hospital.
Look at those clouds.
Wow.
You wanna do it now?
Huh?
I won't mind.
But you'll have to be quick.
Why?
Because...
...I took a shit load of pills.
Pills?
What kind of pills?
Oh, you know.
Pills.
Cassie?
Cassie.
Oh...
Oh, fuck.
You fucking bastard!
Shit! What's wrong with her!
- She's pilled up, for fuck' sake.
- Time to leave.
Maxxie, Anwar, come on.
Nice one, Chris.
Good party.
Guys, can we get going? Just in case
Cassie's like, dying or something.
I normally take her
to the city hospital.
It's miles.
I think she likes you, Chris.
Safe!
Yes, but OK, we have no bus or taxi,
OK! We are stuck, yeah?
We steal car.
Then make fuck, English boy, yes?
Yes.
Come on, find the fucking hospital.
Come on, Tony, we need a doctor.
(Tony) I can't work out the gears.
It's a fucking automatic, Tony.
HORN HONKS
What are you doing?
- Tony!
- Stop shouting!
She's stopped breathing.
OK, there it is.
SKIDDING
HORNS BEEP
- OK, quick. Get her inside.
- Yeah, but what do we tell them?
I don't know, improvise.
Go on, we've got to stash the car.
Come on, what are you waiting for?
Oh, I had such a lovely dream...
Wow.
Get it out.
We can at least some spliffs before
you're taken out and debollocked.
Oh, nice. Thanks Tone.
Relax. We'll sell it tomorrow.
Where?
We just will.
I like the boats. They go places.
Like over the sea and everything.
Are you OK, Anwar?
Shut up. I can't fucking pee
if you're looking.
You're looking, aren't you?
(All) No.
- Who's got skins?
- Er, me. Hang on.
Don't say you haven't got them.
Stop worrying. We've had
all our bad luck for today.
You put them in your back pocket.
- When?
- Come here.
Hang on.
There. Yeah, I got them.
(Michelle) Tony! Tony, do something!
Tony!
Oh, fuck! Oh, fuck!
Oh, my God!
Tony!
I think that could have gone
a lot worse, don't you?
The dope's gone.
At least we've got our health.
That's the important thing.
Chicken feet scratch out a beat
While head rolls on the ground
Lookin' for a piece of meat
And sleep in eiderdown
I walked a million miles
I crawled a million more...
For God's sakes,
what are you doing, Miriam?
Why do you have to get up so early?
Just getting ready.
Anybody would think you wanted
the neighbours to see you.
Do you hear me, woman?
Yes, darling.
Tony.
Yes, Sid.
Chris and that Polish girl.
They got out of the car
at the hospital, right?
I mean, they got out
before the harbour, yeah?
Yeah.
You still a virgin, then?
Yup.