Blessed are those who can give
without remembering, and
take without forgetting.
Amen.
Thanks, Effy, but you know this is
the best birthday present I could have.
A nice family meal.
A chance to have a bit of quality time.
Ah, isn't that lovely?
Ha, you know, this reminds me of
when I was a boy and my Auntie Mabel,
when she was carving the chicken,
she always used to wear
these loose-fitting tops...
Yes, I think we've all
heard this one, haven't we?
It's a joke, Anthea, an anecdote.
And my dad, your grandfather,
God rest his soul,
"What would you like,
David?" She used to say,
and he'd look right
down her front and say,
"I'd like breast, please, and then
maybe a bit of leg and stuffing."
I mean, he'd basically growl at
her. You see, that's a difficult dad.
- No-one thinks you're difficult, Jim.
- Ha! And then Mabel would get to me.
Ah, what could I ask for?
I scoured my brain and came up
with, "Thigh, please, Mabel."
I basically asked for the only thing
I could think of that was non-sexual.
- Thigh!
- Thighs can be sexy.
That's not true.
You'd be surprised, you can
do a lot with thighs, Dad.
No, you can't.
Look, I'm sorry. What
is so sexy about thighs?
I mean, what on earth
can you do with a thigh?
Please not... Not in front of Effy, Jim.
All right. What would everyone like?
A bit of thigh, please, Dad.
No! Not yet! Did I say do it yet?
No, look, Jim! Effy's rolled a five.
Oh, yes, well, er,
right, well, jolly good.
All right, we'll treat
that as your go, Effy.
Er, so you got a five... Oh, God,
I can't understand these rules.
They've translated them from Korean.
Jim, maybe we shouldn't play a game.
Fine. Fucking fine.
Fucking, fucking fine.
So what shall we do, then?
Just sit, shall we?
Yes, we can just sit, yeah, and
I'll see if I can find some nice...
biscuits, ok?
Oh, I hate it when
your mother's like this.
- Help me!
- What's wrong?
Any luck with it?
Never mind.
Good night, love.
Night, sweetheart.
There's nothing there. What's wrong?
'Tony. You all right,
man? How's it going? '
What's everyone doing tonight?
'Um, well, there's a few
people coming round to mine.
'But it's a homework thing, really.'
Is Michelle coming?
'Yeah. Yeah, but it's for
a class that you're not in...
'Um...
'Er... biology...
'You're not in it.'
It's fine, Chris. I'm
not invited, right?
'I just... I don't think you'd
enjoy it, really. You know? '
Yeah. I know.
'I'm asleep or just too bored to
speak to you, so leave a message.'
Is this now officially silent
treatment you're giving me?
Michelle broke up with me, remember?
Still, if you think this is gonna
piss me off, then you're wrong.
I actually quite like it.
I'm just gonna keep on filling up your
voicemail with all sorts of shit...
I'm never neurotic.
Dads always check up on their
baby girls, that's what we do.
Look, she's asleep.
Come on, let's go to bed.
Bed? But it's early.
Panorama.
I don't think that I've given
you my birthday present yet.
- Auntie Mabel?
- Mmm.
Actually, she was a neighbour,
not a real blood relative.
I know exactly what she was.
I'll fetch the turkey baster
and you... wash your bits.
'I dunno. I'm probably not even going.
'You're breaking up, Tony.'
'She doesn't want to see
you, Tony. Leave us alone.'
I wasn't sure what to wear.
Can you believe I borrowed
this top from my mum?
Though Davey, when I wore my mum's
fishnets to the school disco thing,
said that was well rough cos
women used to wear fishnets
without knickers at orgies or whatever,
so, like, my mum would
have got stuff on it.
Davey calls it lady juice. Can you
believe he called it lady juice?
And he says by wearing the tights,
her stuff would have rubbed off on me.
Though I wore knickers,
and I don't think my
mum went to many orgies.
I mean, she grew up in Luton.
I don't think many
orgies happen in Luton.
Don't! He's gross!
I'm a bit scared. Are you scared, Effy?
I keep tasting sick in my mouth.
I think it's cos I'm excited and
nervous. Do you ever get that?
Tasting sick in your mouth, like
you've got hiccups but you haven't.
Do you ever get that, Effy?
Do you?
Did I tell you about
Davey trying to finger me?
Effy! You came!
I mean, cool, I mean...
I wasn't sure you would.
Hi.
It's my last day and they're
fucking wankers to work for.
So you know, break, take, steal...
Anarchy and all that. Mad.
So this is it? Really?
Oh, this is Spencer. A mate of mine.
Hi, I'm Julie and this is
Effy. Do people call you Spence?
No. They don't.
I've heard a lot about you,
Effy. Not all of it good.
You heard anything about me?
Wanna ride?
Shall I get on too?
We're here together!
- Big Issue!
- Bit late for you, isn't it, Kenny?
Last week's edition.
Drunks are usually
too generous to notice.
Who you out with?
On my own tonight. Listen,
you don't fancy a beer?
Sorry, beer's not really my drink.
Now, once you've tasted a Pinot
Grigio, hops just lose their allure.
Right, ok.
Do you want a hand... selling?
Where's all your mates, then, Tone?
Fallen on hard times, have you?
Something like that.
Well, no offence, but the
sooner I get these sold,
the sooner I can get home to
the missus for cocoa and cuddles.
And I'm not going to get much sold
standing next to a posh lad, am I?
Right. Ok. No worries.
See you later.
Ta-ta.
Big Issue, fella?
It's the fucking cops!
Do you think they'll
give us a joint cell?
Hello.
'This is Police Sergeant Bill Hughes.
'Am I speaking to Tony Stonem? '
What?
Clifton Branch police station.
Marjorie Watts. How may I help you?
- Um...
- Sorry, I rushed it. I'll go again.
Clifton Branch police station.
Marjorie Watts. How can I help you?
Hi, Marjorie. I'm here to pick up
Elizabeth Stonem. She's been arrested.
Okey-dokey. I'll check that for you.
Just missed her. Her brother's
picked her up already.
- I'm her brother.
- Her other brother.
I'm her only brother.
Ok, her boyfriend pretending to be
her brother's picked her up already.
She just left with a fat lad.
Ladies, your carriage
awaits. Come on, chop-chop.
Effy! Eff...
That was fun.
Unexpected, but fun.
- So fucking hard to keep a straight face.
- You did well for a fat fuck.
You're so lucky, Effy.
I can't believe it.
Remember when I tried to get arrested
for kissing that police officer?
Normally I would have been with her.
We're always getting into trouble
together at school. Tell them...
Does she ever stop?
Anyone want some?
What is it?
We're known as the cheeky girls.
Not that we're Romanian or,
you know, show off our pants!
'Hi, this is Effy's phone.
She's currently cruising
'at 35,000 feet and there's
definitely turbulence ahead.'
What? It's, uh... Tony.
Effy? What's going on?
Look, oi! Can we get some
concentration here, please?
I know it seems hard,
right, but think about it.
This
- this could lead to, you know, celebrity.
A place in the Guinness Book
Of Records is hardly celebrity.
But it is! Right, I
fucking love that book!
Will you stop eating the tools?
It's not my fault you decided
to go for sugar cube pyramids.
Oh, hi.
What's this... some
kind of retro LSD thing?
Oh, no. It's kinda that homework
thing I was telling you about...
The, er... biology.
Hi, Michelle.
Hello, Tony.
Look, don't worry, I'm not gonna
stay. I just needed Sid for a minute.
- I'm busy.
- Yeah, I can see that, Sid.
Go on.
Let's have a go, then.
Ah...
Fucking hell, guys, you know how
to have a good time, don't you?
I don't want this to be difficult.
If you want to stay, you can stay.
No, it's fine. You made the divorce
terms clear and I intend to stick to them.
Please don't be a bastard.
Look, don't get so upset about it, ok?
I'm sorry I spoilt your
beautiful evening. I'll go. Sid?
Well, go on, then.
Go see what he wants.
Don't feel you have to, Sid.
I'm gonna go.
But only to tell him to leave, right?
You should leave, Tony.
No-one wants you here.
Shit!
You ok?
I tried ringing, but you haven't
answered your phone all week.
- Did you get beaten up?
- Effy's missing. We need to look for her.
Effy? Is this another one of your games?
Yeah, Sid, it's a game.
'Hi, this is Effy's phone.
She's currently cruising
'at 35,000 feet and there's
definitely turbulence ahead.'
This sounds a bit weird, Tony.
It's fine. We'll nick your
dad's car, drive around a bit,
spot her, take her home,
we can go for a pint.
Shit!
What?
It's Cassie.
- She was there.
- So where's she gone?
Flown off on her broomstick?
She's still in the loony bin.
No, she was there.
Maybe she's haunting you, cos she
tried to kill herself because of you.
Hang on. You want to nick my dad's car?
Why can't we nick your dad's instead?
Because, Sid, my dad has central
locking, a sophisticated alarm system
and probably thinks a spell
in prison would do me good.
Whereas your dad has a 20-year-old
car, Neighbourhood Watch
and won't prosecute.
I bet you ten quid I know
who you're thinking about.
There's times I think me and
Tony are gonna get back together.
And just like that, I'm ten quid richer.
There's a sort of thing,
though, isn't there? First loves?
You think Tony loves you?
No, I don't.
Sorry, that sounded far
less harsh in my head.
Don't worry about it.
Michelle.
Wait up. Listen, I'm off to a late-nighter at
the sports club. Fancy coming? A quick drink?
- Can you not take a hint?
- Come on.
You must have worked out
by now that I didn't do it.
You had porno pictures of
your sister on your phone.
How fucked up are you?
- Someone set me up!
- Yeah, right, Josh.
Look, the party'll be a laugh.
Michelle! Please!
Fuck it. Go.
Good decision.
Fucked-up is an understatement.
He's got nice wheels,
though... for a nutter.
Shut up!
- Home!
- This place is fucking brilliant.
It's like Wonkaland.
This is where the rich kids come to die.
Welcome to my world.
I feel a bit rough!
Kevin, I think you should
take Julie to the bathroom.
Come on. Let's get you cleaned up.
Finally, we're alone.
Not quite.
Jesus Christ.
Fuck! I wondered when
you were going to turn up.
Hello, Effy. I'm Jesus Christ.
Anything?
Nothing.
Bollocks!
You know, she may be having a bit
of fun, a joke at your expense.
That's not her style.
No, I know Effy.
She's cleverer than this.
In fact, she's the cleverest
fucking person I know.
I don't know anyone like her.
Cass?
Look, I'm worried about her.
I just... Even if we're looking
in the same places twice...
- Cassie, she was...
- Please, Sid?
Ok.
- Effy?
- 'Hey, Tone.
'You've gotta come to this
party down at Cumberland Basin.
'We're flying the virgin highway.'
- Who is this?
- 'Effy says hi.'
What? Put Effy on the phone!
Hello?
Fuck! Come on, Sid.
Looks a bit... spooky.
You're not still afraid of the dark?
You still sleep with that
night light on, don't you?
It's not a night light. It's a
glow-in-the-dark Batman. It's retro.
Effy!
Effy! Effy! Effy!
Effy! Eff... y!
No, I don't think she's here.
- Doesn't look like much of a party, does it?
- No.
Effy! Effy!
Only if you want some.
Course she fucking wants it.
There we go.
Dr. Stock's marvellous medicine.
Sometimes I think I was
born backwards, you know?
Come out of my mum the wrong way.
I hear words go past me backwards.
The people I should love I hate.
And the people I hate...
Ow! Fuck!
All the help I've ever given you, and
you've been fucking useless tonight.
I've been good.
You've been useless. You're
always fucking useless.
Take Michelle. I worked
fucking hard to create
a shagging opportunity for
you. Then you went pussy.
No...
Instead, she ends up with this Josh,
a complete fucking knob, who I have
to sort, so that's your fault, too.
Sort? What did you do?
Put naked pictures of
Abigail on his phone.
Made sure Michelle could see them.
Made sure everyone could see them.
It was quite funny.
Funny? That's sick.
His sister. Why did you do that?
You know what, Tony?
Sometimes I don't know
why we're friends any more.
It's weird, isn't it?
I'm from Mars, you're from Venus.
I do things, you worry about them.
I sleep with girls, you
persuade them to attempt suicide.
Don't.
Are you bunching your fists at me, Sid?
If you wanna hit me, go right ahead.
Ow!
I said a punch, not a bitch slap!
I can't believe you slapped
me! That's hilarious!
Sid, you'd better not be crying.
I'm not crying cos you punched me.
You're crying for the kids in Africa?
You know I used to so
look up to you, don't you?
Of course I did!
You were at home every night
wanking your brains out.
"Someday I'll be like Tony.
"Someday I'll be like Tony."
And now I can think of
nothing worse than being you!
You've always been selfish,
I always understood that.
You did things because you wanted
something... fine. Makes sense.
But now,
now you do things because you can!
You fuck with people...
and I don't get why.
You've got no friends, no
girlfriend, only your parents left.
Not even Effy is answering your calls.
You're right,
she is clever.
Every time you talk, Sid,
little flecks of spit are
coming out of your mouth
and they're going on my face.
Sid? Sid! Don't be a little girl.
What? Ef?
Who the fuck is doing this?!
Sid. Sid! How the hell am
I going to get out of here?
You're one of them, aren't you?
'Hi, this is Cass.
'Don't bother leaving a message
because I'm not listening.'
I know you're there, Cassie.
I mean, I think I know you're there.
I mean, I want you to be there.
I'm at Rocatillo's.
I want to speak to you,
and I think you want to speak to me.
I didn't have to answer, Tony.
I'm grateful that you did.
- 'Ok.'
- Ok.
'So how come you called me? '
I dunno.
I'll tell you why you rang.
It's because you miss me.
It's because I'm the only
person you can really talk to.
Yeah, Michelle. That's
right, this is all about you.
'Well, isn't it? '
Not tonight. No.
Are you ok, Tony?
No.
What's the matter?
'Effy's missing. Sid's meant to
help me find her but he's fucked off.
'Now I'm at some posh wanker
night at the Ston Eaton sports club
'and I don't know what to do.'
This is the weirdest
fucking night of my life.
What do you want me to do, Tony?
'Nothing.
'I gotta go.'
You know it's, like, two
in the morning, don't you?
You're the one that's been
following me round all night.
You've got a black eye
growing, did you know that?
- Tony punched me.
- Wow! Really? That's excellent.
Is it?
We did a course on it at the
centre... separation anxiety.
He's worried he's losing you.
Well, I just did leave him.
I mean, literally. And then I...
I wanted to see you.
Do you want to kiss me, Sid?
Ok. So this is where you lean in.
Cool.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, I'm usually
better than that. It's...
No, it was lovely.
No, my rhythm was out and my
teeth, they kept getting in the way.
Could I... try again?
Only if you don't ask.
Who is it?
Um, kind of weirdly, Michelle.
Answer it.
Sid? I'm worried about Tony.
'Tony? Don't worry about him.'
I just spoke to him. He
sounded strange, in a real mess.
Michelle, can I ring you back?
He's at some Ston Eaton sports place.
- Where?
- 'Ston Eaton. Something weird's going on.'
I'm in the middle of something.
'You know the sports club? '
The place Josh and his mates hang out.
Please, Sid. Just check he's ok?
Josh?
'Yeah.'
Ok. I'm leaving now.
It's Tony. He's in trouble.
Tony.
- Oh.
- I'm really sorry. I've got to go.
Do you?
Kiss me again.
No, Sid. I won't.
Effy?
Wahey!
- Ok, I'll see your 50 and I'll raise you...
- Raise or fold, man.
- Don't waste my time.
- I'll see you.
Tony. Hi.
Fancy some poker? Five-card stud.
I'm looking for my sister.
Oh. She's over there.
Effy.
Shit. Effy! Hello...
Effy, Effy. What happened?!
Effy, Effy. What happened?
Someone call an
ambulance. Effy. Oh, fuck!
Hello? Yeah?
My sis... Ambulance.
- 'How can I help? '
- My sister's overdosed, I think.
'Can you tell me where you are? '
Where are we? Where the
fuck? Oi, where are we?
I'll give them directions.
What the fuck are you doing?
Ok, let's make a deal.
We'll call an ambulance as
soon as you fuck your sister.
Three from the top, please, mate.
You're joking!
Well, factually it's true. So, um...
no, not a joke. More a funny fact.
Get out of my fucking way!
Don't worry, it's not her first time.
You won't be taking her
virginity. Right, Spence?
She's my sister, you sick fuck!
You put porno pictures
of my sister on my phone
and I make you fuck your sister!
Is this about Michelle? You really
think Michelle is worth this?
I'm so sorry I can't get one
up, I can't... I keep going soft!
Please. Whatever I did,
I'm sorry. I promise,
I'll get you back with Michelle.
I'll do anything, I promise!
Effy.
Josh, mate. Josh.
Shut the fuck up, Spence.
I want you to fuck her.
No, you can't mean that!
- Do you want me to play with it a bit?
- I can't.
- Help you out?
- I really can't.
Then you're a shit brother.
- She's dying over there, Tony!
- I promise...
You'd better get hard!
Please... Please...
Beg me.
I beg you. I beg you, I beg you...
Please...
Well, you only needed to
ask. Here endeth the lesson.
Tony? What's happened?
What the fuck's happened to her?
It's all my fault.
Ok. It's ok. Let's just
get her to a hospital, ok?
* I don't know why I
couldn't feel before
* Faith in a world I
can't believe in any more
* I'm tired of being here
* I'm tired of being wrong
* The universe keeps turning
* Where do I belong?
* You don't remember me
* But I remember you
* I lie awake, trying
not to think of you
* The way I let you down
* The way I did you wrong
* The universe keeps turning
* Where do I belong?
Do you think she can hear us?
I don't know, darling.
Effy, love?
Her hands are cold.
Well, maybe best let her sleep.
She can hear you, Dad.
That's enough from you.
Doctor...
Sorry, is she?
Oh. It's all looking fine. It's
good, yes. I'd go as far as great.
These kids are remarkably
resilient creatures, you know?
It's all gone, and whatever
hasn't will be out in a few days.
One way or the other.
She took some very clean,
pure pharmaceuticals.
Right, ok. I'll leave you be.
So I suppose we should congratulate
you for getting her clean drugs.
You think this was me?
She was with you!
I wasn't, I was...
Don't deny it!
Tony, she's your little sister!
I know.
But, listen... for a second...
No. I've had enough of
listening to you. We all have!
You and your horrid little ways,
always at other people's expense.
Hang on. That's enough.
What?
He loves Effy.
Don't you think this is hard enough?
And who the fuck are you?
I'm his best friend!
And I'm his fucking father!
I know what you are.
Come on, Tony. We're going.
I wanna stay with Effy.
Come on, mate.
Ah! Fuck!
Thank you, Sid.
It's ok. They're free.
No, I mean really, thank you.
Yeah, I know what you mean, Tony.
- She's gonna be ok.
- Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Ok.
Thing is...
I know I can be a wanker sometimes...
but everyone likes that, don't they?
Ball-busting, turning
heads wherever I go.
People like that.
- And I like people liking that.
- We don't have to do this now.
But then...
I start to feel... distorted because...
because I'm more than that.
I don't wanna be a wanker.
I don't, Sid.
Effy knows that.
She loves me for who I really am.
God, I sound like fucking Lionel Richie.
I quite like Lionel Richie.
All I know is,
when I was scared tonight,
and I was a bit... a lot...
I wanted you there.
Effy's different. I sort of own her
cos she's my sister, but with you...
I just really wanted you there.
And then you were in the car.
The thing is, Tony,
you sort of own me, too.
Mostly in a good way.
Come on, I'm taking you for breakfast.
You do know it's 4am, don't you?
Yeah, I know.
Do you reckon we'll find us
anywhere that'll do us a curry?
I've got a real craving for curry.
corrected by chamallow35
www.addic7ed.com