Sid!
Yeah, sorry. It's just there was a...
Now, this is exactly what
I'm talking about, Sid.
Ok? Lack of concentration,
inability to focus, nada commitment.
Now, this piece of coursework
I have marked "ungraded".
Ungraded? What?
I can't pass him with this mark.
Fucking hell!
- Mark...
- Mark, please. With this mark...
Not you, Mark, this mark.
You have failed the entire year.
He's what?
He's failed the entire year.
Sod, you... sidding... idiot!
Ah, hold on, there's no need to panic.
Because I fought for you, Sid, I really did,
and got you an extension.
It was hard, but I worked
at it, and I got it.
- Right?
- Got what right?
No, I got it. Right?
Thanks... Tom.
So... 2,000 words on Lech Walesa,
Solidarity and the collapse of Soviet power.
Jesus Christ!
You've got two days. Get your head down.
You better fucking believe
he's getting his head down.
You can say goodbye to sunshine,
Sunshine. You are grounded.
Put it this way. Let's
change and develop. Ok?
Thanks, Tom. We're all very grateful
for this second chance. Aren't we, Mark?
Yes. Thank you very much.
Oh, yes, my boy! We're
going to do this my way now!
You hear me? The gravy
train has terminated!
Terminated! You lazy little fucker.
- Mark!
- Did Tony fail this?
No.
No, of course not! And
why? Why didn't he fail it?
He doesn't do history.
Right!
You are going to get
something... something right,
if it's the last thing I ever
do. What's your next class?
- Drama...
- Right. Drama. Home. Coursework.
Fucking perfection! Or else.
Why are you talking in
very short sentences?
Emphasis! Drama! Fuck off!
Honestly, Sid, you
know this upsets people.
Sorry.
Just... give it a try, ok?
Ok.
Ok, everyone. Everyone reach.
Oh, Christ...
Reach up. Stretch out your leaves.
That looks so crap, doesn't it?
Go on.
Fuck that.
Why don't you go to the
green and get stoned instead?
No. No, you mustn't.
That would be bad. Bad, do you hear?
And you're a good boy really.
Good. Drama. Fuck it... be bad!
Be good. Drama!
- Fuck it!
- Drama...
Shut up... will you?
- Pretty nice gear, huh?
- Yeah, very funny.
- Where you going?
- I gotta go to this lesson.
Fuck it, man.
- Fuck it?
- Fuck it.
Yeah, let's go.
Right, Donny, you fart
once more and you're out.
Sid?
Hi. Wow, Maxxie, you look all horny.
You can tell?
Sid... I just wanted to
remind you of our date tonight.
Oh... Shit.
Thing is, Cass, my
dad kinda grounded me.
I gotta do coursework.
Oh, wow.
I was really...
I didn't eat for three
days so I could be lovely.
Er, sorry.
Maybe I'll come over and say hello.
I dunno. Maybe.
Safe.
Wow.
Go on, give her one.
That would be so bad!
I bet she bangs like a ferret on acid!
- Hey.
I didn't know which one to
get. They were both so pretty.
Anyway, I got them both.
What do you think? Which skirt?
This goes with my slutty green top.
This one is more virgin.
Yeah?
Tony? Which skirt?
Hmm?
Oh, yeah, it's nice.
Are you listening? I'm asking what
to wear to Tribe Of Frog tomorrow?
Did you ask Chris about pills?
We can have Mitsubishis.
Is that OK, Tone?
Tone?
Wear that one to Tribe Of Frog,
and that one to my choir concert.
- Choir concert? When?
- Tonight.
You and Sid are coming to hear me sing.
Are we? How come?
It just occurred to me
how much fun it could be.
Russia... was... a... superpower...
and...
Er... Lech Walesa...
was a...
Polish... Er...
man... who...
What the fuck did he do? Erm...
Bollocks.
Fuck it.
Right, you have been warned!
Oh, yes, I warned you!
This is what happens.
No telly.
No stereo.
No... Asian Fanny Fun.
That should be enough to
help you concentrate. Is it?!
- Yes, Dad.
- Yes. Thank you.
You'll thank me for this one day.
Oh! Oh, fuck!
What's happened?
I've fallen down the fucking
stairs, you silly cow!
Bugger.
Ah, for fuck's sake.
Ah, yeah. That's better.
Oh, yeah. Ah, yeah.
I'm just gonna go out and
come back in again. Ok?
Would you?
- Hello.
- It's Tony!
Yeah, er, come in!
All right, Sid? Thought
you might need a hand.
With your coursework. Shall
we let some air in here?
Yeah.
That's better. Is that a
picture of my girlfriend?
Wondered where that went.
Right then.
Russia... Lech Walesa...
Jesus, Sid.
The USSR model could be
described as a relationship
of control and manipulation,
but events in the G...
Gdansk.
shipyard in the autumn of
1980 was the beginning of a...
That's some really good bullshit.
Not a problem. Ok, let's go.
Where to?
My choir concert.
Don't tell me you forgot.
I can't. I'm grounded.
Don't be such a fucking vagina.
This is gonna be special.
Anyway, I need someone
to keep Michelle company.
Michelle's coming?
Oh, yes. Nips'll be there.
And you'll wanna see this. Trust me.
Sorry about that. You
won't tell her, will you?
She thinks the world
of you, Sid. Really.
And things run their
course. You get bored.
Are you gonna tell me
what you're talking about?
You'd better be doing some fucking
work. Hi, Tony. How's things?
Not bad, Mark. Is that landfill survey
finished? I'd really love to see it sometime.
Yeah, no problem. Yeah.
Actually, it's quite an interesting
analysis of decomposition rates.
But look, actually, er, Sid's
got some work to do now, so...
Ok. Hope to see you very soon, Sid.
Nice to see you, Mark.
- Bye, Liz!
- Bye, Tony!
What?
Why could you not be like...
Why did I?
Ow!
* I got a date with the night
* Pullin' out my finger
* Gonna catch the kids dry
* Gonna walk on water
* Buying out the fight
* We're sweatin' in the winter
* Both thighs squeeze tight
Ohl
'Mega Dog to the rescue!
Attack, attack! Woof-woof! '
I'm not being aggressive...
Yes, you are.
You're the aggressive one.
Look at you, the Virgin Mary with
your fucking little looks and sneers.
But that's you. Never saying anything.
Leaving it to me to deal with
Captain fucking Calamity up there.
Never backing me up.
That's not true.
The boy's useless,
completely fucking useless.
I sometimes wonder if he's even mine.
Oh, he's yours all right, Mark.
'Mega Dog's trying to tell us something!
'Woof, woof, woof! Woof, woof! '
Hi, Sid. We're just talking.
Right. Talking, yeah.
Get on with your coursework. We
need to do some more... talking.
You see what you've done now?
- What I've done?
- Yes, what you've done.
You stupid, stupid man.
What do you mean, stupid?
Don't call me stupid.
I am not a stupid man. If you would
listen for a second to what's...
What are you doing here, anyway?
Well, I heard "choirgirls" so I came.
Shall we?
I said if they can't fucking educate
her, then I'll take my business elsewhere.
Four fucking grand a term
and the girl gets three GCSEs?
That's the return on my investment?
Where's my margin? What
do they think we are?
Fucking stupid or something...
God Only Knows
Na-na-na-na
na-na...
Where's Tony?
I don't know. Fuck! We'd
better be at the right concert.
No, it's definitely here.
You never need to doubt it
I'll make you so sure about it
God only knows what
I'd be without you...
Beach Boys, man. Fucking top!
I don't understand this. Where is he?
Hold on.
Ah, ah, ah, ah
No, no, no, look, there he is.
'Mega Dog to the rescuel
'Attack, attackl Woof-woofl'
* I may not always love you
* But as long as there
are stars above you
* You'll never need to doubt it
* I'll make you so sure about it
* God only knows what I'd be without you
* If you should ever leave me
* Though life would
still go on, believe me
* The world could show nothing to me
* So what good would living do me?
* God only knows what I'd be without you
* God only knows * God only
knows what I'd be without you
Waa-ohhh.
APPLAUSE
Play, David, play
David, play on your
harp Hallelu, Hallelujah
David, play on your harp
Hallelu...
Hi. I just wanted to...
God! I'm sorry, ok! I'm sorry.
And I need you now tonight
And I need you more than ever...
What the fuck?
Um. Excuse me?
Hi. Just checking Abi's
diaphragm contractions.
What the hell is going on?
The simple act of performance,
sweetie. What did you think?
Bullshit, Tony. You fucking sick...
God, you're such a wanker.
Here...
Fuck you.
Fluffy teddy-bear?
That's my lucky teddy!
And you can fuck off, too!
Well... Michelle. I'm just wondering
why you're overreacting like this.
Overreacting?!
Right in my face, you whore!
You know, typically,
episodes of paranoia
might be symptomatic of a wide
range of emotional and mental issues.
Maybe, you know, you need
some help with the outbursts.
My mother's a psychologist, she could...
Oh!
Ow! I'll kill you, you fucking
flat-chested cocksucking
spastic horse-fucker!
Woah, good swearing.
Bye, Tony.
Later, Nips.
Abi, wonder if you could
give me and Sid a minute.
Yes... I need my medication.
See, told you it'd be worth coming for.
Looks like me and
'Chelle are on a break.
You did that on purpose?
- Go after her.
- What?
Life throws up so few opportunities...
But she's your girlfriend.
- Who you love.
- What?
Change. It's a wonderful thing.
Look, you know how subatomic
particles don't obey physical laws?
They act according to
chance, chaos, coincidence...
They run into each other in the middle
of the universe, and, bang! Energy.
We're the same as that.
That's the great thing about
the universe. Unpredictable.
That's why it's so much fun.
I'm... just gonna go see
if she's ok, all right?
Sid. Bang!
Michelle would never...
never fuck a horse.
Ok, so this line here means you're
gonna live till you're at least 80,
and this line here,
that means you should be careful around
electricity pylons and crocodiles...
- Cwocodiles?!
- That's right.
All right, daarlin'! 'Ad a bad night?
Piss off.
What's your problem?
You giving us cheek?
- No.
- She so is.
Hey, Ems, this girl is being
rude to Char and Shall...
- She's giving us cheek.
- Yeah?
Fuck off out of my way.
You givin' them cheek?
- Cheek...
- She so is.
No.
- D'ya wanna fight?
- No.
Are you givin' me cheek?
What does that even mean?
Hi, Michelle, um, hello, ladies.
Shall we... just let it go, yeah?
Whatever.
Fat bitch.
You fucking what?
Get off her!
Leave her alone.
- Get off.
- Have some of that.
Get off her.
Just get off!
Come on, get off her!
- Are you ok?
- Yes. I'm fucking fantastic
Can I? Shall I?
- You knew... You fucking knew about her!
- No, I didn't!
How could you fucking
not know, you arsehole?
You and your fucking bum chum!
- No, I really didn't!
- Fuck off!
You gave me cheek.
Sorry...
Sorry don't work. You gave her cheek.
Did I?
I'm pretty sure I didn't.
My mate... she gave you cheek.
You give us cheek, too.
You so did.
Is there any possible way
I could avoid a kicking?
You could try talking
your way out of it.
Um, er... ok. Er...
'Mega Dog to the rescue! '
Em! Come on. Happy hour down 'Firkin!
Mate? Do you mind?
- Where the fuck have you been!!?
- Dad, I just nipped to the shops.
For three hours?
I got lost.
- My God, Sid, what happened? You're all...
- No, I'm fine. No, I'm fine. I'm fine.
What's that smell?
Er... Piss.
Yours?
Someone else's.
Right.
You were grounded. You
snooked... snook out.
Snuck out.
You snuck out. You even did
a half-arsed job of that.
It might be better to
do this in the morning.
Did you think we wouldn't know?
Did you actually think
that we wouldn't know?!
Dad, you're such a...
Such a what? Such a... Such a what?
Such a fucking what?
Such a fucking what?!
Dildo.
Oh, fuck the pair of you.
Bed.
Cassie...
What's that smell?
Just piss. What are
you doing here, Cass?
- You invited me round.
- Did I?
I've been waiting. Where were you?
- I was out.
- Who with?
Michelle.
Michelle?
Wow.
- Listen, Cass, I've had a bit of a bad night.
- Michelle's so lovely.
Michelle, my girl
I love her, I love her, I love herl
So hey, wow! Fuck you, Sid!
- Cassie, shh! My parents...
- Fuck you, fuck you, fuck you!
I'm going home.
- No, Cassie...
- Let go... Let go of me!
It's your choice, Sid.
Everything is your choice.
Wake up, Sid.
Bollocks.
Oh.
Hi, Mum.
How's the face?
- Sore.
- Ahh...
Get in. I'll take you.
Cheers.
'Ok!
'Now we're gonna ring up
Lee and we're gonna tell 'im
'that the Government is comin'
round to take 'is babbies away!
'Hello, Lee! '
Mum. Last night...
We were just worried, that's all.
Do you ever feel you know someone,
think you've seen everything they're
gonna do, and then they trump it?
Dad's having a hard time...
- I'm not talking about Dad.
- Oh?
- It's Tony.
- Oh. Tony's lovely.
Thanks, Mum.
Sid, hang on. Close the door.
You know we both really
love you. Don't you, Sid?
I suppose.
I want you to make more of an
effort with your dad in general.
- He's a good guy.
- He doesn't act like one.
Not recently, no.
- But things change, Sid.
- What do you mean?
You...
You need to work out a
way of getting on with him.
It's hard, I know.
Ok?
- I'll try.
- Good.
I'm...
Mum?
Yes.
Anyway, have these... For your eye.
Oh, have this, too.
- You eat too much crap.
- Yeah. I know.
Thanks, Mum.
See you later.
Yeah.
See you.
Sid?
Yeah?
Nothing.
Oh, man, what a goddamn mess
Nobody said this was fancy dress
You're lookin' good
Your hair
Where I'm from you'd be as good as dead
Come on
Get up, get up
Get on, get off all night...
Sid?
Sid!
Sunglasses off, please.
Ok, everybody, well done.
You've all passed!
Everyone except you, Sid.
Cor, mate! What happened.
Nothing. I'm fine, ok?
You've been fighting, Sid.
That's not "Changing
And Developing". Is it?
24 hours left, ok?
You've either got it or you don't...
You haven't got it. Ok?
All right, Tom. Sorry I'm late.
Yo! Last night, man. Cool. Total blast.
Everything you could
want from an evening.
Songs, choirgirls, colourful
costumes, fellatio... Rabbits...
- Rabbits?
- Look, don't ask, man. Yeah, so, Sid...
Woah! Was that Michelle?
No, er, there were these girls...
What kind of girls, Sid?
Big ones.
I thought you was
hanging out with Cassie.
Er... Bit of a mix up.
Yeah? Like what?
She was really looking forward to that.
Ok, everyone!
Because you've all given it
everything, you can go early.
But use the time wisely, ok?
Woah, woah, woah, sailor!
Not so fast. A little
you-me time, yeah?
Sooo...
Coursework?
- Ready for tomorrow?
- Yeah, I'm, like, halfway through.
Sid, there are people
here you can talk to.
I am here for you.
We can sort this out.
I'm all ears. Come on.
What? We can sort out the fact that
my best mate wants me to make a
move on his girlfriend, who I love,
even though she still loves
him and now actually hates me?
My Dad thinks I'm a complete fuck-up,
and can't stop acting like a fuck-up
and no matter what I try, I
can't stop pissing everyone off?
We can sort that out, can we?
Ok. Ok, yeah.
Give me a moment to, um...
Life, Sid.
There are lots of ups and downs, ok?
It is like a...
It's like a... bird, flying.
Find your wings, Sid.
Right.
And do your fucking coursework.
Otherwise you're fucked.
Yeah. Thanks, Tom. That sorts it.
Pas de probleme, Sidney.
So see you tomorrow.
Don't leave me hanging, G.
Safe!
- Hey. All go according to plan?
- No.
- Ho! That girl can really swing.
Your mistake, my friend, was
making your move too quickly.
What?
Yes, grasshopper. Sensei say
that boy must wait 12 hours
before he approach girl on rebound.
This is fucked up, Tone!
Isn't it?
- Don't you want her?
- I told you. It's a gift.
You fucking freak me out sometimes.
But it's never dull. Is it?
No.
Ring her. Take her for a
drink, and see what happens.
What's the worst that can happen?
It's your choice, dude. Your choice.
Ah, fuck.
'Hello? '
Hi, Michelle. It's Sid.
- 'Fuck off. I don't want to speak to you.'
- 'Chelle...
'You heard me! '
- I'm sorry, all right? I'm sorry.
- 'Wankers! '
Yeah, I know, and I
wanna see you so I can...
'What? '
Please. I wanna make it up to you.
- 'Fuck off.'
- Can I talk to you?
'Talk about what? I don't want to.'
Yes, I know, and I want...
'I can't take your shit, you
and Tony. You wanna talk? '
Yeah, yeah. Please, Michelle.
'I don't want to talk. I'm
tired. You both fucked me over.'
Meet me at Ronny's Bar, I'll explain.
'Explain, yeah... '
Please, 'Chelle, I wanna see you.
Hi.
- Thanks for coming.
- That's ok.
Why weren't you at, um, college today?
Snap!
- Some right hook, that girl.
- Yeah.
Believe me, 'Chelle. I didn't know
he was pulling a stunt. I promise.
I promise.
What was that for?
For forgetting that you and
Tony are different people.
Is that easy to do?
Well, you come as a package,
but you're...
sweeter.
Nice.
Ah, shit.
I'm one of the nice boys.
Fantastic
I like this one.
I love you.
Huh?
Nothing.
Let's dance.
What?
Dance with me. Come on.
Come on.
Michelle, I've been a
bit silly, haven't I?
'Hello! '
Cassie? Hello, I've got your...
- 'Hello? '
- Who is that?
- 'What's that noise? Hello? '
- Hello? Hello?!
Is Cassie there?
Sid?
Oh, God!
Oh, Christ, she's done something!
'What? '
Why?
You've really got no
idea? For fuck's sake, Sid!
'Jal, wait? Where are you going? '
Where do you think I'm going?
Shit!
- Is she all right?
- She will be.
What have they done to her?
- Pumped her stomach.
- What?!
Why have you chose to
start caring about her now?
It's a bit fucking late. You're
the last person she needs right now.
Why? Why is this my fault?
All you had to do was go on
that fucking date. That's it.
But...
You need to be
relatives. Are you family?
- No.
- Yes, I'm her sister.
- Right. Is he your brother?
- No. He's not.
Hi, Sid.
Dad, what's going on?
Dad?
Er, your mum's... gone.
Gone? What do you mean, "gone"?
She packed a bag and
went to Auntie Rosie's.
Something she "has to do".
She can't live here any more.
She can't talk to me any more...
Hang on. Have you split up?
Oh, God, no, no.
So she's just not living here
or talking to you any more?
Yeah.
Right.
She said to tell you "sorry".
Why is she sorry?
Isn't her fault, is it?
Relationships are complicated...
and sometimes, you know...
You shouldn't blame yourself.
I don't blame myself. I blame you.
I know, and, you know, you have...
Shut up! Why did you let her go?!
Sid... I can't...
Because you're fucking
useless, you sodding idiot!
You stupid bastard. You
fucking stupid bastard!
That's my fucking mum!
And she's fucking gone!
- Sid, I'm so sorry...
- It's a bit late for that.
You've got to ring her.
- It won't do any good.
- Ring her! Or... Or...
You're fucking grounded
until you get her back!
- Huh?
- You fucking heard me!
Say goodbye to sunshine, Sunshine!
- Sid...
- I've got things to do!
* Put it behind you
* The hurt is gone
* Forget everything...
Can I come in?
* That you've done
* Time's movin' on
* Time's movin' on...
It'll be ok.
'Hey, Sid. Where'd you get to?
'Sid, hello?
'I know you're fucking there, mate.
'Come on, it was just a laugh.
'Don't be a fucking pussy.
'Sid, come on. Sid! '
corrected by chamallow35
www.addic7ed.com