Whoa... Chris.
It's not true, is it?
What?
They're aII the same
size at action stations.
No...
Poor Chris.
Wow.
That's better...
CooI.
< Sami AIIahu Iiman hamidah.
Rabbana wa IakaI hamd.
AIIahu Akbar.
Sami AIIahu Iiman hamidah.
Rabbana wa IakaI hamd.
AIIahu Akbar.
< Rabbana wa IakaI hamd.
Anwar?
Yup.
What date is it?
13th. What's up?...
AIIahu Akbar.
I think MicheIIe's
parents are back today.
Bummer.
Do you think I shouId remind her?
I'm trying to pray
to my god here, Cass.
Oh... wow...
Is he Iistening?
I hope not.
Otherwise he knows about aII
those piIIs I necked Iast night.
Sing quietIy.
Yup...
AIIahu Akbar.
Cute.
CheIIe...
Fuck off, Tone.
It's me, Cass.
Crazy bitch.
Yes.
Never fucking eats.
Right, but... MicheIIe...
Your mum gets back today... yeah?
Tomorrow.
Today's the 13th. Isn't it?
Mmm. Tomorrow.
Oh, heIIo, Cassandra...
Hi, Anna!
HeIIo, um...
It's MaIcoIm.
MaIcoIm, yeah, wow.
How was the honeymoon?
It was just wonderfuI, wasn't it babe?
Just us and 47 Namibian nomads
out there in the desert... Heaven.
CooI.
We do Iove a nomad, don't we, babe!
So have you been
heIping MicheIIe cIear up?
Oh, wow, totaIIy.
I expect she toId you about my
important meeting today?
CIients coming to Iook at
my curtain designs.
Right, can we get in?
I want some fucking Coco Pops.
WeII, IoveIy to see you again Cassandra.
You're Iooking much better than
the Iast time I saw you. WeII done.
Oh... You too.
Nice to meet you again, Martin.
It's MaIcoIm...
It's MaIcoIm.
For fuck's sake!
What's she on, hunger
strike or something?
Sshh!
MicheIIe, darIing, here we are,
safe and sound.
Ahhhhh! What the fuck!
Mum! You didn't teII me!
Go go go... Come on, JaI...
HeIp...
Go!
I forgot my T-shirt.
GIGGLING
Ah! Oh, oh...
I want to eat you, fuck bunny.
Oh... Oh... Oh!
Whoaa!
Cassie...
How you doing, kiddums?
You had some breakfast?
Oh, yeah. MicheIIe's does crazy
bacon, egg and sausage sandwiches.
They're mad.
There! Great!
I'm going...for a shower.
LittIe wittIe!!
Do you want me to...feed Reuben?
Oh, wouId you, sweetie?
I've got so much I've got to do...
< Hey!
LittIe wittIe.
< Margie...
Thanks, poppet...
It's my finaI cIinic day.
They'II sign me off if
I've gained a haIf kiIo.
Oh, yeah? Have you done it?
TotaIIy... For sure.
Hey... Hurray!
< I can't find the..uh...stuff!
< Coming!
LittIe wittIe,
wittIe, wittIe, yeah.
OK. Yes.
AII changed and cIean, yes.
LittIe wittIe,
Iook what we got for you. Look.
Greedy boy... Greedy boy.
MUFFLED GROANING AND BUMPING
< Oh, right!! Right!!
< Right a bit...
< Bit more...
MOBILE PLAYS GENTLE TUNE
RHYTHMIC BUMPING
AND MUFFLED SHRIEKING
TEXT ALERT BEEPS
GROANING AND BUMPING CONTINUE
MUFFLED SIGHING
Hey...
Kiddums! Oh, cheerfuI!
Thanks. I feeI great, Dad.
Course you do... What do you think?
Oh, wow!
Amazing.
CooI.
Did Reubens do his poo?
Oh, Yes.
He's Iike aII changed and asIeep.
Ah, thanks, that's super!
The taxi's here.
Taxi?
They send it from the cIinic
to make sure I go.
Yes, of course.
They're signing her off, darIing!
Fantastic!
We knew you'd make it through.
WonderfuI!
And don't forget to say thank you.
Oh... I wiII...totaIIy.
PurpIe. I'm thinking, purpIe...
Yes...
Ah yes... Yes.
OK, my beautifuI.
Show...me...
the money...
You got enough room
back there, Cassie?
You wouIdn't teII on me,
wouId you, AIan?
You know me, kid. See no.
Hear no. Speak no.
They'II sign me out
if I'm haIf a kiIo up.
Do you know what you're doing?
Oh, totaIIy... I'm so fine...
I'II miss you, Tiny...
Oh, wow...
Yeah...
You too, AIan.
You gonna eat this time, Cassie?
TotaIIy.
Hey.
Don't give me the smiIe.
Not that smiIe, OK?
OK, AIan.
Love you.
I Iove you too, Tiny...
Change of music?
Sure.
It's my new favourite.
Can I see your pockets?
880 grams each.
Neat.
That's over
one-and-a-haIf kiIos, right?
1 ,760.
Sorted.
I need to be quick.
Christ, I wanna wizz.
Busy... Wait, pIease.
Oh, fuck!
Get out off the fucking toiIet!
Weight is correct.
''Demeanour...
Satisfactory.
''Attendance, Interaction,
CompIiance... Yes, yes, yes.
''Mood...yes...''
How's your mood?
Oh... Fantastic. ReaIIy.
ExceIIent!
PHONE RINGS
Yes?
No... No...
I don't care who's going, AbigaiI.
You faiIed to compIy with my wishes
regarding parties
and carpets were damaged.
Stop crying!
I am not an ''expIetive'' bitch.
I am your mother!
Have you taken your medication?
WeII, take it now...
Now!
So...
before you Ieave us
to start your new Iife,
it's important that you understand, um...
- Cassie.
- Cassie!
That if you are troubIed again,
then you treat us
as a pIace of safety and refuge.
We Iike to think of Restoration
as a big famiIy you can re-visit
any time it's necessary.
Here's my card with
the emergency number...
CaIIs after six are doubIe.
We're aII on your side.
Providing you have arrangements
in pIace for the fees.
How does that sound?
LoveIy. I'm so gratefuI, reaIIy.
Good.
Thank you, Carrie.
You may go to Group CongratuIations.
Dr Stock.
Thank you so much.
APPLAUSE
WeII done, Cassie.
We'II miss you. Won't we?
Wow. Thanks everyone.
Right... Who's next?
Madison.
Can we congratuIate you?
No, I'm not happy.
You!
You're staring at me.
No-one's staring at you, Madison.
Are we?
(Group) No... No...
Now. What's been troubIing you?
I keep teIIing myseIf that maybe
I'm a bit over-sensitive, you know,
and it's... It's starting to work.
There's no more...
no more voices going,
''Ba ba ba ba ba,''
no more voices whispering,
you know, ''Ba-ba...''
And then... And then...
Spit it out Madison.
We're here for you, aren't we?
(Group) We are...
PerfectIy straightforward
business deaI, right?
This kid asks me for credit terms
and I'm Iike...
''trust''...
Yeah?
WeII done, Madison.
The onIy thing that I ask...
is repayment...
in a cIearIy defined scheduIe.
So I give him what he wants.
What did he want?
Goods and services...
This fat fuck.
This deceiving, scheming
IittIe pIuke!
He thinks...
that he can get away
with cheating me out of my money...
Maybe he wasn't trying
to cheat you, Madison.
Oh, yeah?
It's a misunderstanding.
ReaIIy?
We need you to work on this,
Madison.
WeII, I'm working on it!
I'm working on it.
Er, chips, pIease.
Few more.
Just a few more.
Cheers!
Hi, Marnie.
What are we?
PiIchard.
Cute. What we saying?
We're saying we're an oiIy fish,
tasty and rich in heaIthy
Iife-giving Omega fats.
Sodding Jamie OIiver.
Bummer.
Go on, then.
You sure?
Yes, why not, I'm into Iong Iife.
Cheers, Marnie.
See you Iater.
Smart-arsed bIonde fucker.
AII right.
- AII right, Sidie boy.
- Kiss me, you fooI!
Yeah, white boy!! Wha gwan. Rrraas!
You get me!?
Dis bIood him Iubed up, man!
White boy got bear shit
on him forehead and ting!
What's the frequency, Kenneth?
Sorry.
Got a bit carried away there.
I think you did, man.
Oh, do stop it, OK?
It's not funny.
Can I sit here?
Yeah, sure, go for it.
Oh, cooI. So nice of you.
You been home, Sid?
No, came straight from MicheIIe's.
You Ieft before her mum
caIIed the poIice?
Yeah.
Went a bit wrong.
Then Tony had to go and Jujitsu
Mr MicheIIe's cos...
WeII, because he's a totaI
fucking wanker reaIIy.
You Iove Tony.
Pardon?
I said, you Iove Tony.
You aIways taIk about him.
Do I?
I mean, it's cooI you've
got someone to Iook up to.
Oh, it was fun.
Throwing aII that food around.
Just Iike, throwing it everywhere.
Wow. Wow!
Whoa.
You must be hungry.
Yeah. Bit of a hangover and... Yeah.
There.
Go on then.
You gonna eat that?
Oh, totaIIy.
I'm better now. I'm totaIIy better.
How do you do it?
What?
Come on, Cass.
I mean you never eat anything.
Your parents must notice
or something.
I dunno.
I Iike you, Sid.
OK.
So I'm going to show you.
You have to do a Iot of taIking.
I'm good at taIking.
You do that whiIe you're cutting
things up a Iot. Then, questions.
Where's your Student Card?
Sorry?
Your ID, have you got it?
No I, er, Iost it
somewhere Iast week.
Change the subject.
This is great.
I Iove these sausages.
You shouId try one. Go on.
DeIicious. Mmmm.
Hang on you didn't...
You're not quite sure what I'm on
about but I keep distracting you.
Then I up the ante.
Yum. I Iove this stuff.
ReaIIy deIicious.
You're reassured I want some more
and I'II keep waving it at you
untiI you stop Iooking at me.
Where did you Iose it?
Sorry?
Your ID. I mean, they won't Iet
you use the Iibrary, wiII they?
God, I've gotta go.
Oh.
I'm so fuII.
Gotta dash.
There you go. Job done.
That's impressive.
Cheers.
But aren't you kind of, you know,
Iying to everyone?
I'm so better.
I got discharged from the cIinic.
Seems a bit fucked up.
What?
I said just seems a bit
fucked up, that's aII.
Oh, wow.
But you see...
It's Iike nobody's fucking business.
And it's not exactIy
Iike anybody cares, so...
I care.
Look. PiIchards. CooI.
And I got it from a fish Iady.
Yeah, I wasn't so keen on them.
What you fucking taIking about?
Omega fats and fishy oiIs,
they're cooI.
I was just chatting to Cass, Tony.
Hey, Cass.
How's dippy worId?
She's better. She just got
discharged from the cIinic.
Yeah, whatever. Jesus!
What?
Don't you ever wash?
That's Iike Iipstick.
Yeah, man, the essence of woman.
WeII, one at Ieast.
So who's the Iucky Iady?
That's Iike someone kissed me.
I can't beIieve you haven't
washed man. You stink!
Somebody kissed me.
WeII, yeah, mate,
that's a totaI fucking operator
error cos you stink.
I didn't have time.
Time? I've been home, showered,
done my Chi, had a wank,
subtIy undermined my dad,
put new cIothes on and here I am
with my EngIish coursework.
EngIish coursework. Oh, fuck!
Sometimes I wonder why you even
bother to get up in the morning.
You're such a compIete fucking
waste of time and... Ahh, shit!
Wow, Tony. Bummer. It Iooks
Iike you pissed yourseIf.
That's not supposed
to fucking happen.
Look at Tony, man. Ah, shit man!
Raas bIood white boy gone
piss himseIf up you get me!
Mandem's sick stains. Hey, Cuz!
Yo got serious stains!
Him cream up his pussy good styIe.
I'm a bad person.
Come on!
< That hurt, actuaIIy!
Gotta go. Sure you have.
Finish off the rest of my
food if you want.
OK.
This guy from my group
therapy's got your ID card.
And he's a crazy fuck and he
hates you because you cheated him.
What's his name?
He Iikes to be caIIed Mad.
Twatter.
Yeah. TotaIIy. What did you do?
I bought some dope on the tick,
and then we Iost it
in the harbour and...
Oh, fuck. Fuck.
Tony!
This is a room for femaIe staff.
Yeah. The drier's broken in ours.
Ah, there you are.
Jesus, we're in troubIe!
That crazy fucking deaIer
found us, Tony. Hi, Angie.
We gotta do something. I mean, you
couId taIk to him and... Oh, fuck.
Oh, you wankers.
That was weII funny, man.
But someone's gonna have to apoIogise
cos Kenneth's crying now so...
Oh, Jesus Christ,
HoIy Mary, Mother of God!
That's Angie! Don't Iook! Get out!
For fuck's sake! Fuck off!
< Sorry, Angie.
You stiII got it.
Get out of there
and don't Iook at her, aII right?
You Iike me. You Iike me.
Look up if you Iike me.
Oh, bugger.
Shit!
Oh! Sid.
Hi. Sorry, Angie.
You shouIdn't go into
the staff showers, Sid.
I know, I know.
It was a crisis.
WeII, it's just a bit
embarrassing that's aII.
ActuaIIy, I'm pretty
confident about my body...
No, I'm having a crisis.
Oh.
WeII, sometimes aduIt bodies can be
a IittIe overwheIming.
Oh, for Christ's sake, Angie,
I don't care about your tits!
Oh.
I'm in deep, deep, deep shit.
Right.
OK.
You need advice?
I need advice and 300 quid.
Otherwise someone's going to
be re-possessing my boIIocks.
OK, weII Iook, when it comes to debt,
the best thing to do is to face up
to it before it gets out of hand.
Yeah?
Yeah. AII you have to do is go
to the person you owe money to
and caImIy ask them to
rescheduIe the payments.
RescheduIe payments?
So that's one baII now
and then the baIance next week.
BeIieve me, Sid,
I'm a responsibIe aduIt.
I know. OK?
Now what was it,
a phone or something?
ActuaIIy, Angie, it was three
ounces of prime hydroponic skunk.
Shit!
Yeah, shit.
Go to the poIice.
They'II arrest me.
Give it back.
I Iost it in the harbour.
Keep your head down.
He's got my student ID card.
Right.
Right. OK.
BasicaIIy, I'm fucked, aren't I?
Yep.
WeII, thanks, Angie,
I feeI a Iot better now, yeah.
Look, give me a moment. I'm sure
I can come up with something...
No, sorry.
Chris.
Mm-hm.
You've come to apoIogise, right?
Huh?
To say sorry.
Oh, yes. Erm, yes, I'm sorry.
Sorry I saw your boobs.
Sorry I saw your bum.
Erm, sorry I saw your...
ApoIogy accepted, Chris.
Right.
WeII, I've got work to do.
So if you're done...
Yeah.
Chris.
You shouIdn't Iook at me Iike that.
Sorry.
It isn't appropriate.
I'm your teacher and...
Have you aIways had that moIe?
Um... Yes.
It's IoveIy.
Oh, God.
PHONE BUZZES
OK, right, everybody, Iisten up.
I'm gonna be taking in
your assignments today.
Why are you so reIaxed about this?
So he's got your ID Card.
So what?
Um... everybody?
So what? He's gonna cut
my fucking boIIocks off!
ChiII out, Sid. I'm chiIIed, right?
Why are you so chiIIed?
I'm confident and reIaxed
with my abiIity to improvise.
I'm going on a course
for the rest of the week,
and I'm not going to be here.
AIso, I didn't buy the drugs.
You did.
Nice one, thanks, Tone...
Guys, Iook... We've got a suppIy
teacher coming in for next week
and in fact, he's on his way up
from the office now to say heIIo.
Everybody...
Look. There's 3,000 students at
this coIIege. He won't find you.
So if you give me your assignments,
I promise that I'II have them
marked for you by the...
Hi, can I heIp?
SuppIy teacher!
Oh, Hi. Hi. Hi. We reaIIy
appreciate the short notice.
Everybody this is Madison.
Madison...
..Twatter.
CHUCKLING
PhD.
Nice to meet you, Tom.
- You got a probIem?
- No, no...
Because, er it's been a whiIe
since I...taught...
I just... I just wanna say that it's
a beautifuI, beautifuI thing to do.
Right. Um...
Right, so you'II start next week?
No. No, I've aIready started.
I don't know,
checking Iists and things.
Checking Iists?
Yeah. Who's who and
what's what and bIah bIah.
I'm reaIIy Iooking forward to,
er, to meeting you.
Oh, I'm beside
myseIf with excitement.
I'm totaIIy beside myseIf.
(Anwar) Sid.
Sid. Look at me, man.
Oh, God.
What's happening for Christ sakes?
His fucking deaIer's
a suppIy teacher.
Oh, God.
So?
So he's gonna cut
Sid's boIIocks off.
(Anwar) Sid.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Sid. Sid. I'm going to tap you, OK?
Oh, God.
Maybe a bit harder.
For Christ sakes!
Right. It's a probIem but Sid's our friend and
we're going to soIve it, OK?
Got that, Sid? We're gonna
put our heads together
and come up with a soIution.
Sid. We're here for you. We're
thinking of the answer right now.
Anyway, I've got socioIogy so em...
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
Don't we have to go
over your French, yes?
Yeah, we shouId go.
Hang on.
We're going to give this some
serious thought, yeah, guys and... OK?
We can't just Ieave him Iike this.
We'II get back to him.
Yes, that's it. OK?
See you Iater, man.
We're gonna
get back to you on this, Sid. OK?
Mum?
This is Sid - your son.
Listen, I've got a probIem.
CouId you ring me back pIease?
BEEPING
Sid. Are you OK?
Bit fucked up as it goes.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Yeah.
It's Iike totaIIy kind what you're doing, but it
won't make any difference.
Huh?
The texts you're sending.
The messages...
What are you on about, Cass?
I've got a few probIems
here of my own, you know?
I know, but...
Thanks anyway, for trying.
Cassie, I haven't been
sending you any messages.
I just saw you.
There aren't any messages on here.
What?
There aren't any
messages on your phone, Cass.
I thought...
I thought you Iiked me.
What?
Nothing.
BABY CRIES
HeIIo.
Yes, it's Cassie.
I think I need to see you again.
Hi.
HeIIo, kid. What's up?
I'm having a few probs.
Oh, Cassie. I'm Iistening.
There's somebody I Iike.
I thought he was
sending me a message -
texts and things, but he wasn't.
What was the message?
''Eat.''
Right.
It wasn't you, was it, AIan?
I don't teII you what to do,
Cassie. I'm just a taxi driver.
So, Iike,
who's teIIing me to eat?
Who wants you to eat?
You got permission.
I haven't got a knife and fork.
You don't need them.
No.
What kind of day did you have?
Fine.
Have you got any more good tunes?
I Iove you, Cass.
I Iove you, too, AIan.
So eat.