Previously on X-Men...
Mister Sinister!
You want our son. Nathan!
It's a Techno-Organic Virus strain,
and the virus
is already spreading rapidly.
What if there's a cure
in yours, Bishop?
This band only got enough juice
for Nathan and I.
Meaning we can't go with you.
My next life will be mine.
Take care, Jean.
Call me Madelyne Pryor.
Charles Xavier entrusted me
with his dream,
and it does not ask you to love
or embrace my kind as your own,
but merely to accept
that this is a shared world
and that my kind
have the right to live in it.
We will begin talks to admit
the mutant nation of Genosha
into the United Nations.
Maybe we should take a page
from the Professor's playbook
and give Erik a second shot.
Do you think your team
would still trust you if they knew?
Was it caused by atomic testing?
Or is it nature herself,
deciding the time has come
to change the human race?
Some say they're freaks,
some call them monsters,
but all over the planet,
they are known as mutants.
We prefer to see it as a world
that misunderstands us.
Fortunately,
helping us build those bridges
is a journalist as esteemed as yourself.
Well, I am just as flattered
to be sitting with a renowned scientist
such as yourself, Doctor McCoy.
Blue blushes, too, my dear.
Here in Westchester County
sits an unassuming English estate,
the X-Men's home.
A school for mutants,
founded by the late
Professor Charles Xavier.
Not like regular boring classes.
More hands-on learning, you know?
But with big death machines
and vampire dinosaurs.
For many of the X-Men,
Xavier's school
is the only home they've ever known.
People who have fallen through the cracks.
Forgotten.
Desperate to belong.
But that sense of belonging
goes worldwide today,
as the UN formally admits
the mutant nation of Genosha.
This is taking forever.
Gambit, please remember
that should the new Blackbird
suffer a malfunction,
you are the only soul on board
for whom gravity
would most certainly be an issue.
Can it, you roosters.
Look-y ahead.
Ki-yay!
They be busy doing a bit of renovating
since Gambit's last visit.
Whoa!
We have to stop
at my favorite stall for a...
Is that the X-Men?
My friends!
Well, would you look at you, girl!
Lot of smiles at the mansion
when we heard Madelyne Pryor
scored a top spot among Genosha's brass.
The Interim Council wanted an X-Man.
Luckily, you guys could spare a Jean.
Hush, madame.
Two always better than one.
And far better than three.
Most times.
Forgive Gambit's passive adolescence.
He insisted on coming
after Rogue agreed to join me at the gala.
I confess, the master of magnetism
was surprised
to receive an invite
bearing the United Nations' seal.
Yeah, I hear it's called "the future."
Magneto, the Interim Council
would love a word with you
before tonight's gala.
Privately, if possible.
Hmm. So where the heck does that leave us?
- Ha-ha!
- Dang!
I'll be a wet bird on a live wire.
Kurt Wagner, how the heck are ya, furball?
We shall play tourist
as the Council speaks with Magneto.
Kurt joined the Council
to help work with Genosha's
various communities of faith.
Things to see!
Such wonders in this city.
Long as he left those faithful
killer monks of his back at the monastery.
Ah, a scimitar tongue, Gambit,
you remain as always.
We have much to discuss
since our gothic adventure amid the Alps.
Come.
Everything around us
would not have been possible
without the work of the X-Men.
Oh, my!
It's just like he said it'd be.
Who? The Professor?
Uh, yeah, sure.
Always used to say
we'd have a place all our own one day.
More than a place.
A home.
Daddy's charging pretty high rent.
Birthing a nation overnight
is not without its share of stumbles.
Ignore him.
Fly can't help but ruin honey.
Or maybe Gambit's willing to ask questions
no one else will.
Like, why is Magneto suddenly mutant MVP?
For a man named Gambit,
your poker face is very poor.
Hey, mind your beeswax, furball.
Didn't go ringing for no priest.
It does not take a priest to see you
and Rogue's souls touch in every gaze.
Ain't the touch
she be looking for.
You Americans.
So theatrical.
Life is violins und close-ups.
I blame soap operas.
Just marry the belle and be done.
Scoundrels like me,
we don't get no white picket reward.
We too busy for love.
Too busy sinning.
There is no love without sin.
For love is best measured
in what we forgive.
I am here with Scott Summers,
also known as Cyclops.
Scott, are you surprised
to see such a bold move in world politics?
Well, if being an X-Man
teaches anything, Ms. Tilby,
it's to expect the unexpected.
I always kept that in mind
as field leader...
Those shades
are weirding out the lights.
Can you take 'em off?
I can't. Sorry.
So, back as team leader...
Actually, let's talk about you
and Marvel Girl.
I hear you're the X-Men's power couple.
A love that spans galaxies.
So I have to ask,
when did you know she was the one?
You're skipping the questions, too?
Hard to interview someone
who can't tell which parts
of her memories belong to her
and which parts belong to her clone.
Even reacquainting myself
with my psychic powers feels
strange.
Like the face of an old friend
seen from every angle
but the one in your memory.
This busted mug
ain't changed in a hundred years,
and you know it.
I remember so many things.
So many with Scott.
You two lovebirds still ain't talking?
He's grieving his son.
Although, the way he's avoiding me
recalls a time.
We were in Nevada.
I had just acquired the power
of a cosmic entity.
The Phoenix.
Oh, right. You were there.
I asked Scott to go on a picnic at sunset.
She seemed nervous
when I asked her to go out.
Like she didn't trust me.
He was scared.
Afraid the Phoenix had changed me.
I wanted to reassure him.
I wanted to show her
that nothing had changed.
She was still the hothead
who knocked my books out of my hand
when I ran into her
on the first day of school.
But I could already
feel the universe speaking to me.
Much like Scott used to
through our special psychic rapport.
She snaps at me,
and then she takes off my ruby glasses,
which hold back my powers.
I needed to anchor myself
because every fiber of me
hungered to leave
and travel the cosmos right then.
And nothing happened.
Jean was using the power of the Phoenix
to block my optic blasts,
and we could see each other's eyes.
They anchored me.
Focused me.
His eyes made me stay.
Now...
I know all about drowning in memories.
Best to look up and keep paddling.
Keep moving, 'cause the past'll
yank ya under if ya don't.
I forget how many sunrises
your eyes have seen.
They only ever seen one of you, Red.
Just the one.
Logan,
- I'm...
- You're Jean Grey.
He's Scott Summers.
Those are the rules.
You just forgot 'em for a sec.
Enough said.
Now go talk to that overgrown Boy Scout.
Now, the latest adventure, parenthood.
Jean...
Jean and I don't have any kids.
You don't?
No.
Strange.
I saw hospital records
for one Nathan Charles Summers,
born to Scott and Jean Grey Summers
just last month.
Born at Westchester Memorial?
I spoke to a Dr. Brians there.
He said you told your teammate,
told Rogue...
That jerk wouldn't deliver my...
He called my kid a freak.
Scott, I came here today
to give the X-Men a chance
to show the world
that mutants are just like us, people.
Normal.
And you lie.
Why lie?
Because you're normal.
Excuse me?
I said, because you're normal.
You're ungrateful.
We fight, risk our lives for you.
Evil mutants, robots, crazy aliens.
I gave him up.
I gave him up
because you can't say thank you.
Because I have to stomach your questions
and prove that I'm a person.
I lie because the truth is
we're nothing like you.
Thank God, because it's the only reason
you people are still alive.
Recent events have aligned themselves
in an unprecedented fashion for our kind.
With even the most overlooked of us
finally getting a voice.
We need to be thinking about
how to speak loudly
as one united community.
This concerns me and my X-Men, how?
We need a handsome jawline
that begs trust and respect.
A poster child king.
Careful, Ms. Frost.
Don't go filling this man's head
with such notions.
Whose charitable idea was it
to let a human be on the Council?
Were no others available
to weep over semantics?
Moira's a fierce ally to mutants.
And we all agreed
on the title of Chancellor.
You eclectic allotment
of social climbers
wish for me to rule Genosha?
Hilarious.
One could argue, and many sadly do,
that none of us would be here today
were it not for you
and your publicity stunt.
Are there no others better tempered
to stomach the squabble
of human diplomacy?
But Charles be gone, Magneto.
And I may not like it,
but if Charles trusts you with his X-Men,
he'd trust you with this.
We were at a bar in Germany
when he first mentioned his dream.
I laughed at him.
Was he sentimental or suicidal?
Both earn an early grave.
He did that smile of his,
that annoying secret smile.
"Magneto, any dream worth having
is a dream worth dying for."
We thought we'd perish
before seeing the day
when humanity accepted our people.
Like Moses and the Promised Land,
we would carry the dream,
but never live it.
Look, Magnus,
I may not be Jean Grey,
but I know what the Professor
would say if he was here.
"Time to dream bigger."
You shall have me on one condition.
I ought to knock you
from here to the North Pole.
You think making me your queen
means we're getting back together?
It is a political calculation, Rogue.
Me, mutant kind's fiercest defender,
and you, an X-Man whose touch
allows her to feel anyone's pain.
A true leader, an empathetic one.
Was this your plan all along?
Make everyone like ya and then take over?
This was Xavier's design.
It is why he gave me his X-Men.
A final chance to uphold the promise
we made to one another so long ago.
But I need help.
You take me for a fool.
Acting like this is all about you
and the Professor.
I won't deny my passion for you.
As with Gambit,
loving you makes broken men whole
so that even as you deny us,
our heartache is not in vain.
We would be lucky to have you lead.
I can't believe
I lost it like that.
Oh, Scott, anger is normal,
even for mutants.
Sometimes you just have to let go.
There are some things
worth holding on to.
Describe him to me.
Describe Nathan.
I see him everywhere.
In every face,
on every street, so clearly.
I can't see color, but up here...
I see these big brown eyes
and his wild rust-colored hair.
It reminds me of...
Of us.
Don't tell me you can explain.
Jean!
If you'll excuse us, Madelyne.
Something wrong, Miss Pryor?
Sorry, mind just drifted a moment.
Mind drift indeed.
Communicating via psychic rapport
was our thing, Scott.
Just stop and let me explain, please.
Explain what? I know what I saw.
- Jean, you...
- How long has it been happening?
A month maybe. I was checking in
after she moved overseas,
- but we ended it...
- Go.
Go to Genosha. Be with my clone.
Oh, dear.
What you saw on the astral plane
was confusion, Jean.
Grief.
She's the mother of my son.
That's the one thing
I can be certain about right now.
Do you love her?
I love both of you.
Whole galaxies beckoned me.
But I turned my back for you.
Sinister cuts out a part of me
and you love it?
That wasn't love in there, it's ego.
The music is changing
and you need a chair.
Leader, father, husband...
And you? You don't trust your memories.
Do you even love me?
My love for you
is the one thing I remember
amid this pain and insanity!
Remember? Or feel?
Choose, Jean.
Do not spin this on me.
Do you love me, Jean?
Or am I just a lovely memory?
Jean! What is it?
Hey, there.
Wasn't expecting a lady caller.
What's wrong, chère?
You best sit down.
It was back after I ran away
from my daddy.
My evil mother
was helping me with my powers,
said she knew a fella who could help.
An associate.
The man seemed nice enough.
Seemed to wanna help.
Just not like I thought.
He spent weeks
talking about how mutants were special.
How we'd have our own cities
and culture one day.
He even had plans, too, Remy.
Mutant art, fashion, dance.
He showed me that being a mutant
wasn't just about my power.
It could be something more.
And when we realized
that his electromagnetic powers
protected him from my touch,
other things started happening.
But then I started seeing the hurt in him,
like raging waters.
There wasn't enough room in our affair
for his demons and mine.
When I joined the X-Men,
Erik said he wouldn't want me
to lose another family.
He acted like it never happened.
We both did.
You gonna accept his offer?
If Genosha's shown us anything,
it's that we don't need
to be afraid of change.
And if I can play a bigger role
in bettering the world,
well, that's the whole reason
I became an X-Man.
You never wanted
to make things official.
I respected that.
I played the swamp rat.
And I played your chère.
All the expectations,
every time looking at you,
seeing all the things I couldn't do.
Like telling Gambit
the dang truth?
I can't touch you, Remy!
Your heart may beat for me,
but I can't feel it.
You light up everything you touch,
but never me.
Some things be deeper than skin, chère.
Not this.
I wager that fool
will break your heart in two.
Gambit always knows the odds.
That it?
In this game, he do.
Till then, we be friends, mon amie.
Just friends.
A drink for my dashing Cajun?
Not enough drink change the fact
that others be more dashing, chère.
Assemble the Council. We need to talk.
Whatever is the matter, Dr. Cooper?
Is it your dress?
My former prosecutor
has likely taken issue
with your choice for Chancellor.
But surely Genosha's right to self-govern
will not only be protected but cherished,
as it is with all UN nations.
Most other nations don't allow a terrorist
to be their leader.
Yet so many allow their leaders
to be terrorists.
If it eases your mind,
Magneto accepted only on the condition
that we ask one of the X-Men
to govern with him.
Rogue.
What did she say?
Oh.
Turn it off. The music.
- Jean, what is it?
- Madelyne.
Thanks for the dance, sugar,
but Remy was right.
Some things are deeper than skin.
Turn it off, the music.
Get everybody out.
Kill the music.
Cable?
You have to get everyone out.
- Now! He's coming.
- Who's coming? What's going on?
Access failure imminent.
Body slide one.
No, no!
Not again.
Your eyes.
You made it.
You survived.
I'm so sorry, Mom.
Sorry for what?
What in tarnation.
- Rogue, get to the gardens.
- Hurry!
Terminate mutant.
Rogue!
Remy.
He alive.
So are you.
Gambit, how many?
Too many.
So many.
Some vile Godzilla Sentinel.
You go at it, you end up dead.
Can't even dent it.
We're trying to evacuate folks now,
but the Morlocks, they stuck in the bay.
Right under its belly.
And there's no way to them.
A promise was made.
Hurry. Almost to the gardens.
Mutants located.
I draw its fire away from the gardens.
Rogue clears a path for Gambit
to the Morlocks.
Save as many as you can.
We shall not live our days wondering
if we could've saved more.
Never much cared for roulette.
Then how about we spice up them rules?
They shall be avenged!
Don't worry.
Leech knows Callisto will find us.
If not her, Magneto.
He promised Leech
would never be scared again.
The X-Men are no friends to the Morlocks.
Mutants located.
Bonne soirée, mes amis.
Now, kindly follow me.
Omega-level threat detected.
No.
It's too dangerous, chère.
Don't you dare, Erik!
You hear me?
He's trying to protect us, Rogue.
Do not be afraid.
Omega threat eliminated.
Gambit see your bet and raise it.
'Cause the cards always be in my favor.
Mutant intruder neutralized.
The name's Gambit, mon ami.
Remember it.
How many?
How many, damn it?
To reiterate
for those just returning to us.
Regardless of your stance
on recent world events...
Oh, my.
The images you are about to see
may be disturbing.
Sugar.
I can't feel you.