Previously on X-Men...
The mutant leader's
assassination last year
by former NSA agent Henry Gyrich
has spurred increased sympathy
toward mutants.
The team,
they'll always be family,
but with the baby coming,
maybe it's time to think of a life
beyond the X-Men?
How'd scum like you get your hands
on Sentinel technology?
You freak shows think
we wouldn't find a way to evolve, too?
I know who we need to see
to find Bolivar Trask.
The man who killed Charles Xavier.
Gyrich warned me
you were coming.
The last will and testament
of Charles Francis Xavier.
Everything he built
now belongs to me, my X-Men.
Workers have unloaded
all passengers save one
in what has become
a Coney Island nightmare.
Any sudden moves
and the wheel could come crashing down.
It's okay, honey.
Come to me nice and easy.
Real slow.
Ladies and gentlemen, I...
Art?
Is that who I think it is?
Saving humans?
But while it's too soon to tell
how recent events
will impact mutant-human relations,
one thing is clear
to both humans and mutants.
I don't get it, Jean.
Did the Professor not trust me?
Maybe we're seeing this wrong.
Maybe he did this for us.
Across the globe, reports are flooding in.
Mutants and humans aided and saved
by the former mutant terrorist
who had gone missing
after failing to launch a mutant rebellion
following Charles Xavier's assassination
last year.
And we're hearing
the international community
is closely monitoring the situation,
with some demanding
this unlikely savior
answer for his past crimes.
This is our home, you pig,
it's all we have left,
all you dogs left us.
You think regular folks can sleep
knowing you demons are down here, lurking?
Please, don't hurt Leech.
The depths you humans go.
Even denying these outcasts
the indignity of your waste.
Electricity and magnetism
are intimately acquainted.
How unfortunate for you
that I am the master of magnetism.
Dirty mutant.
You'll get what's coming...
You're him!
- You're...
- Magneto.
And I promise you, child,
you shall never be afraid again.
What was the Professor thinking?
"The only safe and sure way
to destroy your enemy
"is to make him your friend."
Mark Twain.
Beast isn't wrong.
The Professor had a plan.
Seen a lot of futures,
but Magneto leading the X-Men?
That's a new one.
Maybe we go change it back, huh?
Look, plenty of us at this table
have paths so dirty
they don't squeak
no matter how much spit you got.
Maybe we should take a page
from the Professor's playbook
and give Erik a second shot.
I have arranged for the Morlocks
to travel to the mutant nation of Genosha.
It saddens me that none of you,
nor Xavier himself,
thought to use
his considerable finances to do the same.
But this is one of many mutant matters
on which we can
and will improve, my X-Men.
Guess we can assume
- those jerks in the sewer are...
- Alive, but not unharmed.
The tragic fact
that I did not consign those sapiens
to the waste bin of history
is proof of my desire
to honor Charles Xavier's dream
of mutant-human...
...coexistence.
Okay, prove it.
Let Jean scan your mind,
see your real plans.
Scott, no.
What? You did it with Gyrich.
I accessed Gyrich's mind for information.
Using my powers
to assess honesty is another matter.
Even if I sensed
Magneto's intentions were sincere,
that's today, this hour, this minute.
Then we check every minute of every day.
I was under the welcome impression
that you and Mrs. Summers were leaving us.
Not a chance.
I'm keeping an eye on you.
Scott, read the will again.
Like it or not,
this is what the Professor wanted.
Please,
my intentions here
were not to cause drama or discord.
You must understand.
You have been our fiercest foe for years.
A desire for you to prove yourself
is only natural.
And Storm,
you are the closest thing to a goddess
as we will ever see.
So, I do not lightly deny your request
and demand your trust instead.
Xavier wanted this.
Maybe he was wrong.
After all our tête-à-têtes,
you have finally realized
what I did ages ago.
Even Charles Xavier can make a mistake.
Haven't worn this old thing
since that battle
in the Blue Area of the Moon.
I was possessed
by a malevolent cosmic entity
intent on consuming all of existence.
But there was Scott,
fighting by my side.
You are afraid
that he will no longer leave
now that Magneto has taken charge.
Can I tell you something?
I need to tell you something
and I need you not to judge me
too harshly.
Or tell Scott.
You have my word, Jean.
There are times
when I think about the baby,
his future, and I...
If he's a mutant,
how do I tell him he's different?
That the world
will remind him of it every day.
That he must always be careful,
always be on guard, or else...
You wish him to be born human.
I have wondered
what it would be like to be human.
It is a tempting daydream.
But then I remember how my mutant gifts
brought me to this mansion,
to this family,
to a sister.
Thank you, Storm.
Just ever since
I was in Gyrich's mind,
I can't shake this feeling
that something terrible is coming.
Boy, I sound like a fool.
No, Jean.
You sound like a mother.
Well, your little pep talk
went about as smooth
as a dozen cats in a yarn store.
I wish to be alone, Rogue.
Ugh! Giving me the heebie-jeebies,
pouting with that old bucket of yours.
Back when we were friends,
I would always sense Charles in my mind.
Not invading, more a presence.
I was in his thoughts and he in mine.
When we parted ways,
I told myself I needed this
to protect myself from his psychic powers.
But you were worried
if you still felt how much he loved you,
you wouldn't be able
to go through with your crusade.
And yet, here you are,
dragged in like a kitty cat's prize.
Xavier's sacrifice
brought about a world
more tolerant towards mutants.
I am indebted to honor his last wish,
even if his X-Men won't trust me.
Perhaps they are right not to.
My past is too littered with error.
Mine was, too, remember?
But the X-Men still took me in.
The thing is,
I didn't go about demanding their trust.
I earned it.
I feared you would do your best
to avoid being alone with me, Rogue.
Do you think your team
would still trust you if they knew?
That was a long time ago, Erik.
And that cat's got to stay in its bag,
you hear me?
Ready yourselves, my X-Men.
We don't lose our cool
when the good guys show up.
You were saying?
We're here for Magneto.
Think twice.
Our rifles are resistant
to your electromagnetic powers.
I should have thought twice?
Magneto, by order of the UN Commission
on Superhuman Activities,
I hereby place you under arrest
for crimes against humanity.
You will stand trial
at the UN Headquarters.
Should I successfully vindicate myself
in what I will generously assume
is a fair trial,
will I earn your trust?
That is how due process works.
Then...
I yield.
These acts prove Magneto's guilt
beyond any doubt
and offer a preview of the zeal
with which he would resume his quest
to dominate this planet,
should he be exonerated today.
Justice is overdue.
Any updates?
Cooper's listing every nasty step
Magneto's taken from here to Asteroid M.
Folks outside are pissed
he's even getting a trial.
Can't say I blame 'em.
Have you seen Scott?
He's there with the others
making sure Magneto doesn't pull
one of his stunts.
Oh, he didn't tell me.
Lot of that going around lately.
- Down with muties!
- Down with mutants!
Come out here, cowards!
People will look back on today
and say it was the beginning of a new age.
The day mankind made Magneto pay.
Folks out there want the UN's heads
just as much as his.
Stir the pot, boys,
and keep 'em distracted.
I'll only have one shot.
The defendant may now speak.
As a boy, my people's homes
were burned to ash
because we dared
to call God by another name.
Then, my people hunted me
with those who had once hunted them.
I was a freak, born a mutant.
An abomination to their misnamed gods.
In history's sad song, there is a refrain.
Believe differently,
love differently,
be of different sex or skin,
and be punished.
We sing this song to one another.
The oppressed become oppressors.
Xavier knew this
and dreamed we could change, find harmony.
A future where human and mutant
could relinquish the past and finally...
You claim justice is overdue.
Indeed,
but so is healing.
Your words, while kind, do nothing
to heal those hurt by your crimes.
And your sound-bite indignation
will not heal mutant wounds.
You build robots to hunt us,
collars to chain our power.
Humanity must protect itself.
Protection?
That is extermination.
I have only ever acted
to avenge crimes against my people,
as you act to avenge
those against yours today.
If that were the case,
are we truly to believe, then,
that in the face
of what you consider to be extermination,
you would walk Charles Xavier's path?
Not the worst thing,
this don't go Magneto's way,
don't you think?
They've broken through the barriers.
We can't hold 'em back.
Deploy smoke! Deploy smoke!
Protesters are breaching the perimeter.
They must want Magneto.
And the judges, ma'am.
What in the blazes did we do?
You gave a monster a trial.
Now, you are traitors to your kind.
Oh, to play by the rules
and still they come for you.
Storm, watch Magneto and the judges.
The rest of us will back up the guards.
Our goal is de-escalation.
- Protesters are demanding...
- Jean, gotta get into the city.
Crowd's lost their blasted mind.
Logan,
he's...
He's here.
Who? Apocalypse?
The baby!
Oh, crap.
Careful, Logan!
Get out of the way!
Hang tight, Jeanie.
Almost there.
Can't hide forever, you freak!
No more mutants!
Rogue, secure the perimeter outside.
This way to the traitors!
I am unable to ascertain
the nature of the weapon on his back,
but his armor
is constructed from an energy-resistant
titanium-laced alloy.
You got a name?
X-Cutioner.
Here to make sure gene freaks like Magneto
pay for their crimes.
Darn mutants!
Get 'em!
Round two. Absorb this!
Hurt my friends?
Well, now you answer to me.
Humanity answers to no one!
Know what I hate about your kind?
You act like you got it so bad.
Normal people have it hard, too.
Harder!
We just have the dignity
not to whine about it.
You see? It's the whining.
I hate your whining
just as much as I hate you.
Scott, hurry!
Jean, you're in pain.
The baby's coming, Scott.
Storm, Jean's in labor.
Morph's here, but they're losing the line!
Rogue, fly Cyclops to Jean immediately.
Magneto and I will protect the judges.
Be careful, Storm.
It's still Magneto.
Circumstances do not offer us a choice.
I need your men stationed at every door.
I want those in the lobby
to assist the other X-Men.
You, uncollar Magneto. You...
- Well, now who does she think she...
- Do not think.
Be silent. Heed my commands
and you shall survive.
What do you mean,
"don't do mutant births"?
You people can lose control
of your powers.
And if she needs a C-section...
I'll show you a C-section, bub.
Jean.
Darling, I'm here.
This doctor won't deliver our baby.
Rogue, can you use your powers
to siphon his medical expertise?
Excuse me? Do what?
Cyclops, if I slip
and touch your baby, my powers...
Rogue, I trust you.
We both do.
Enough! You all need to...
Sorry, sugar.
Prep an IV and get this lady to a room.
- Found you, muties!
- Go! Go! Go!
Filthy muties!
Magneto.
Get 'em!
Be animals
and be caged!
Let us see how their mob manners
fare against the shock of good conduct.
Magneto!
Storm!
Ahh!
The breeze is gone.
I cannot feel it, nor the moisture,
nor the air.
What has he done to me?
Magneto, this was not what we wanted.
Lies.
This is your dream.
My kind splayed before you,
powerless and afraid.
All the X-Men have done
is use their awesome power
to protect a world
that hates and fears them.
Behold their reward.
What must we do to be good enough?
Is this the high road's destination?
If so, I say,
as I have too many times before,
never again.
No!
Let us go! No!
Oh, dear.
Bigot,
ingrate,
sycophant, worm.
So small I could smite you with a step.
There was a time I would smite you all
for what was done to Storm.
But today,
I have saved you from your own,
for an old friend has challenged me
to remember this view of Earth.
How vast it is
versus how small we make it.
Charles Xavier entrusted me
with his dream,
and it does not ask you to love
or embrace my kind as your own,
but merely to accept
that this is a shared world
with a common future,
and that my kind, like yours,
have the right to live in it.
I am trying to be better.
Please...
Do not make me let you down.
Look, he has your eyes.
Well, doesn't he need a name?
I was thinking "Nathan."
Yeah.
That's my boy, Nathan Summers.
Nathan Charles Summers.
The United Nations
stunned the world this week
when it issued a pardon for Magneto,
due in no small part
to the former mutant terrorist's efforts
in saving the tribunal
and quelling the insurrection.
In another gesture of goodwill
in our efforts to improve relations
with our mutant brethren,
we will begin talks to admit
the mutant nation of Genosha
into the United Nations.
- Poison?
- Dark roast.
Genosha, a UN nation.
Never thought I'd see the day.
I hear you and Jean
have begun to make arrangements to leave.
Does this mean you trust me
to carry on Xavier's dream?
The Professor trusted you,
and I trust him.
I guess that'll have to be enough.
If I may offer advice, Scott.
Be wary.
Be vigilant.
Tragedy lures with fortune first.
This was a good week for our people.
Yet it was not without cost.
Inhibitor collars use radiation
to temporarily neutralize
our mutant powers.
The X-Cutioner's laser rifle
fired a concentrated dose
of that same radiation.
It affects genetics on a cellular level,
suppressing a mutant's abilities
without the need for a collar itself.
Ororo...
How long?
- Additional tests will be needed before...
- Hank, please.
How long?
The effects appear permanent.
We'll fix this.
Scott and I aren't going anywhere, okay?
Not until you're well again. I swear.
Beast, we need to contact Muir Island.
Jean, my sister.
You of all the X-Men
know the heartbreak of saying goodbye,
having said it so many times.
So I ask
that you help the others understand
why I could not stay to say it this day.
My faith in your family's future
is strong.
And I cannot rob you of a bond
you have more than earned.
It is human nature to crave connection,
as it is also mutant nature to be heard,
seen,
to feel another soul finally seeing yours.
Connection is a fragile treasure.
One we sacrifice so much to maintain.
Only to then sometimes
watch it break in a blink
that changes your life forever.
We are no longer connected, Jean.
And now we walk
in two very different worlds.
But trust that I will cherish
what we shared as X-Men,
memories that already feel
like a lifetime ago.
"Like another woman's life.
"Or another person's dream.
"Love, Ororo."
If only I hadn't left the UN,
I could have...
You did what you had to.
Storm did the same.
And we will respect her decision.
That so?
The blast had your name on it.
Should be you leaving, mon ami.
I don't buy it.
Not one minute.
Storm will spend a day
schlepping it with the basic folk
and come right home,
happy as a...
Ha! What did I say?
She's back!
Jean?
I need the X-Men.
What? Jean?