-Oh! I've got to save the princess.
Hey, where's the Bowser?
He's usually in here.
[Orange laughs]
What was that?
Sounded like it came from over here.
Princess? Toad?
-I'm not a toad. I'm an orange.
[laughs]
-Whoa... what did you do
with the princess and Toad?
-Toad?
Is that like a frog?
-No, is more like,
you know, mushroom.
-I know him.
He's a "fun-guy."
[laughs]
-All right, enough of the funny stuff.
Are you ready to a-fight?
-Not really. I'm kinda hungry.
-Well, then try out one
of my spicy meatballs.
-[laughs]
Meatballs?
More like you're throwing boogers.
Stop throwing boogers,
Mr. Pick-and-Flick.
-Is not a booger, and
I'm not Mr. Pick-and-Flick.
I'm Super Mario.
-SpaghettiOs?
I love SpaghettiOs! [laughs]
-No-no-no-no-no, it's Super Mario,
not SpaghettiO.
-Uh-oh.
-What do you mean, uh-oh?
-Uh-oh, SpaghettiOs. [laughs]
-[frustrated groan]
Fireball.
-Hey SpaghettiOs,
use a Kleenex already, geez.
-Well, you no-good two-bit orange.
-Two-bit?
I'm at least eight bits. [laughs]
-[groans]
Don't make me take-a my gloves off.
I can get-a real mean when I want to.
Just you ask my brother Luigi.
-Did you say linguini?
Your whole family's made of pasta.
You have a sister named Ravioli?
[laughs]
-[groans loudly] You tell me
where the princess is or else.
-Or else what? Shell?
-Shell?
What are you a-talking about,
you crazy orange?
-Turtle shell. [burps]
-Oh!
-Whoa! SpaghettiOs is bite-sized.
[laughs]
-Oh great, you a-shrunk me.
You're like a big orange Rick Moranis.
-Oh, don't worry, bite-size SpaghettiOs,
it could be worse.
-Could be worse?
Now I'll never find the princess.
How could it possibly be worse?
-I don't know. Bullet.
-What?
-Bullet.
-Huh?
-[Orange laughs]
Ohh... Super Mario.
More like Stupid Mario, right guys?
[Peach and Toad sigh]
I defeated Bowser and
saved you guys hours ago.
-Yeah, if by defeated Bowser, you mean
you annoyed the living crap out of
him until he just got angry and left.
-Whatever, Princess Apple.
-That's Peach, thank you very much.
-You're an apple. [laughs]
-[frustrated sigh]
-Hey, you guys are still here?
I told you already, get out
of my dungeon, you freeloaders.
Captioned by SpongeSebastian