♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive ♪
♪ She is saving our future
By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear
She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
[Ridley] Happy Herd Day.
[humming]
Hey there.
Happy Herd Day, Fred.
Oh, a special banner just for me?
We wanted to show you
how much we love you on your big day.
We're all here for you, dude.
Speaking of dude, where's Dudely?
[groans] Sorry I'm late.
I couldn't decide which tie screams
"Herd Day!"
Also, what exactly is Herd Day again?
Oh, sorry, didn't mean to scream that.
It's only the most important day
of a bison's life.
It's when you go from being
a baby bison to a full member of the herd.
And you do that by leading your herd
for the very first time.
Wow! This is the tie for that.
Let's not forget the party
the bison are throwing in Fred's honor.
It'll be so fun. My Grandma Dottie
is bringing her world-famous hay cake.
Rad. It's not a party without cake.
I can't wait for you to meet my grandma.
She's the toughest bison there is.
And I know tough.
Grandma always says,
"Lead with your heart."
The best way to lead a stampede
is by being yourself.
That's true.
And you are the expert at being Fred,
so I know you'll do amazing today.
We'll be by your side
the whole time, Fred.
It's gonna be the happiest of Herd Days.
-Definitely. Follow me, team.
-[cheering]
I can't believe I'll soon be galloping
at the front of my own herd.
Check out this bisonic move.
[Ismat] Wow.
I call it
a "triple-hoof double axel herd toss."
-You're one of a kind.
-Impressive.
-[all gasp]
-Oh, let me guess.
Is this called a "double axel earthshake"?
I don't think that's Fred.
[Dottie] Yoodle-ay-hee-hoo!
Whoo-hoo! Hi-yah!
Grandma Dottie!
Come here, my tough little potato kugel.
It's been too long, kiddo.
That happens when you're leading stampedes
all around the plains.
You're basically famous.
Well, I do hold the plains record
for strongest stampede,
longest yodel, and fiercest fur-do.
But this day is about you.
Ready to train with your favorite grandma
before the big stampede?
So ready.
My friends
are gonna join for the training too.
Hi, nice to meet you, Dottie.
I'm Ridley, and this is the Eyes Team.
What a bisonic group of pals
you've got here.
Ooh! I love a bison with style.
Oh, this old thing?
It means Grandma's a strong bison leader.
So cool.
I can't wait to watch you coach today.
I wouldn't miss it for the world,
and I brought my famous hay cake.
♪ Da, da, da, da ♪
Happy Herd Day, Winnifred.
[gasps]
Come on, follow me
to the stampede practice.
Uh, I'm confused.
I thought it was your special day, Fred.
Me too. Who in the galaxy is Winnifred?
[groans]
Everything okay, Fred?
Well, the last time I saw my grandma,
I used a different name and pronouns.
That was before I discovered
that "Fred" feels more like me.
You're a Fred through and through.
I didn't realize
it was so long since we saw each other.
Now Grandma doesn't know I've changed.
She still thinks I'm her granddaughter
instead of her grand… Fred.
Well, do you feel ready to tell her?
I do want to, but maybe not today.
I gotta focus on the stampede.
This is a big day
for me and Grandma Dottie.
You do what's best for you, Fred.
Don't forget, we're here for you.
Thanks, Ridley.
-Now, let's pick up the pace.
-[laughs]
[all] Whoa!
[whistle blows]
A successful stampede
excels at three herd-tastic traits:
strength, agility, and endurance.
-[all grunting]
-Ah!
How about the art of not falling?
[laughs] That too.
We'll practice all these skills
before you lead the herd.
First up: strength.
As the leader,
you need to be strong
against any testy weather.
Now go lead the herd to that tree.
Follow me, everyone.
Remember, the best way to lead
is to be yourself.
Be myself.
Uh, yup, got it.
Whoa!
You need a banana?
It might be an ice pop now,
but it'll help you be ready for takeoff.
No, thanks, Peaches. You got this.
Follow me.
[all] Whoa!
[screaming]
Yes!
[all cheer]
Agility time.
Sometimes in a stampede,
you have to change direction
without slowing down.
You're a rock star, Dottie!
[sighs] Focus, Fred.
[grunts]
Leaping runs in the family, kid.
You're gonna ace this.
Thanks, Gran.
Go! Go! Go!
-Mummazing!
-You got this!
-Superstar!
-Way to go!
Almost there. You could do it.
-Lead with your heart, Winnifred.
-Huh? Whoa!
That was a close one. Come on.
Let's move on to the next challenge.
Grandma Dottie… [groans]
Are you okay, Fred?
Before, you were leaping
all over with no problem.
Oh, I guess I'm distracted.
I think I would feel better
if I told Grandma Dottie about my name.
We're royally here
for whatever you want to do, Fred.
Grandma Dottie seems like one cool bison.
You think it's okay to tell her, right?
Yeah. My grandma has an open mind
and a big heart.
Then you should totally dino do it.
I think what we're saying, Fred,
is if you're ready, we support you.
Thanks. I do want to talk to her. I…
Come on, my little herdlings.
Let's move those hooves.
…just don't know when the right time is.
Endurance is important in a stampede.
You got to keep going,
even when things get tough.
Holy smokes.
The frozen banana's
turning into a barbecued banana.
Still good, though.
[gasps] I thought I wasn't
gonna have to do anything today.
I didn't dress for physical labor.
Dudley, I'm carrying you.
Yes.
And even just watching you
is making me tired.
[grunts, groans]
Um…
-Hm? Time-out.
-[whistle blows]
Ms. Jones, could you lead
our happy herd back to the plains, please?
-Of course, Coach Dottie.
-Oh, finally. I need a break.
[Ismat] Again, I am the one carrying you.
I notice you seem
a little off in your game, my baby babka.
-And I think I know what's going on.
-You do?
Yipperee. I'm pushing you too hard.
Oh, no, Grandma Dottie, it's not that.
I love your coaching.
It's just, I haven't been feeling… myself.
Oh dear, that's the most important part
of leading a herd.
I know what might help.
You know how my pin signifies strength?
Well, my grandma gave it to me,
and now I'm passing it on
to my granddaughter.
Granddaughter? Oh, but…
Grandma Dottie,
there's something I got to tell you.
[man over P.A.] Attention,
Dottie and Fred. Take your positions.
Oh, you hear that? It's go time.
[groans]
Fred, the ceremony's
in T-minus two minutes.
Did you get a chance
to talk to Grandma Dottie?
No. She's so busy with Herd Day…
I get that.
When my dads need to talk
about a royally important matter,
it can be hard for them
to demand an audience.
But I think the reason she's so focused
on Herd Day is that she loves you a lot.
Yeah, that's true.
I feel ready.
I'm gonna go tell Grandma right now.
On my Herd Day,
I'm gonna lead the herd as me: Fred.
-Way to go.
-You got this.
Oh, there you are.
Are you ready for your big moment?
Almost.
There's something I need to tell you.
Really? But it's time to start.
I know, but this can't wait any longer.
If I'm going to lead the herd,
I want to do it as myself.
After all, you always say
to lead with your heart, right?
Well, my heart says that the way I feel
most myself is to go by the name Fred.
That's because I'm non-binary,
and Fred is the name that fits me best.
And I also use they and them,
because calling me a she or a he
doesn't feel right to me.
Oh. I didn't know that.
No wonder you've been struggling.
How could you lead the herd
without being yourself?
I'm sorry I used
the wrong name and pronouns.
Thank you for showing me your heart.
That's how I know
you'll be the greatest stampede leader.
My sweet, tough Fred.
Thanks, Grandma Dottie.
Now let's stampede!
[cheering]
They're leading with their heart.
♪ Check me out ♪
♪ I am heading up the whole stampede ♪
♪ In the way that no one else but Fred
Could ever lead ♪
♪ I will lead with what's inside me ♪
♪ That's what leaders do ♪
♪ Just be you ♪
♪ Be the truest you ♪
♪ Look at them
They're a true bisonic superstar ♪
♪ And I'm proud to know
The bison who they truly are ♪
♪ You are Fred
'Cause that's what fits you ♪
♪ That's what feels most true ♪
♪ Just be you
Be the truest you ♪
♪ There is no one else but Fred
Who you should ever be ♪
♪ Thank you for sharing
Who you are with me ♪
♪ Though it isn't always easy ♪
♪ You will make it through ♪
♪ Just be you
Be the truest you ♪
You were right, Ridley.
This did turn out
to be the happiest of Herd Days.
And it's not Herd Day
without my world-famous layered hay cake.
Happy Herd Day, Fred.
Oh, thanks.
-[gasps]
-[both] Hoof Dance time!
[all] Go, Fred. Go, Dottie. Go, Fred.
It's your Herd Day.
[theme music plays]