♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive ♪
♪ She is saving our future
By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear
She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
[Ridley] Ms. Peabody, I Presume?
Bye. See you next time.
-Thank you.
-[girl] Museums rock!
Oh, hi, Mr. Peabody.
I don't like your tone, Ms. Jones.
But tonight, I suppose
you'll finally be useful.
I need you to keep my niece entertained
while I do artifact inventory.
Apparently, she doesn't find
spreadsheets exciting.
[scoffs] Youths.
-Hey.
-So, you're a Peabody.
Penelope Presley Peabody.
But you can call me Penny.
Nice to meet you.
Ridley Jones, protector--
I mean, resident, of the museum.
Oh, I know.
My uncle's told me tons about you.
I think it's so cool you live here.
[gasps]
Is that a real lasso?
Uh, yeah, it is.
Wow! Have you ever used it?
Once or twice.
That is awesome!
If you think that's awesome,
you're gonna love what else we got
in the museum. Come on, I'll show you.
Okay, team, let's run through
our party planning checklist.
Uh, balloons and banners are a go.
Party supplies are handled.
Tonight, everyone has horns.
-[chuckles]
-Party horns, that is. [snorts]
And I got the super-important map
you told me not to lose right here.
[gasps] Uh…
Huh. I mean, now it's right here.
-Thanks, Ralph.
-Mummazing.
That leaves Dudley.
Do you have tissues for when you start
crying?
I can't believe it's our little Ridley's
100th adventure already.
They grow up so fast.
Listen up, everyone.
I planned Ridley's surprise party
to perfection,
so there will be no surprises tonight.
Except for, you know, the surprise.
[chuckles]
Got it?
-Totes.
-No surprises.
And this is our butterfly display.
-Aw. Look at their cute little wings.
-Don't. They're ticklish.
I mean, uh,
we're not supposed to touch the exhibits.
-Oh sorry. Oopsies.
-[giggles]
Did you hear that?
Uh, no. Anyway, come on.
You're gonna love the Egyptian wing.
Let me just look to make sure
it's clean before we go in.
Surprise!
Happy 100th adventure, Sunshine!
For the big one hundo,
we're going on a radical treasure hunt.
-[laughing]
-[gasps]
They're alive?
"Alive"? What?
No, these are museum animatronics.
[making electronic sounds]
Oh, uh, same.
I'm totes a robo dino. [grunts]
Ouchie ka-wow-ie!
That's no robot.
Okay, yes, they're alive.
But it's a really important secret.
They're my friends,
and I have to keep them safe.
Will you pretty please not tell anyone?
Well, well, well.
Wait till Uncle Peabody hears about this.
He knew something
was up with this museum.
Good thing he sent
his favorite niece to go fishing.
-Not cool, dude.
-[all gasp]
You tricked me.
I thought you were different,
but you're just like Mr. Peabody.
Don't take it personally. My uncle always
says it's every Peabody for themself.
He'll be so proud
when I report back with this dirt.
A museum that's alive?
Now that's interesting.
Please, please don't tell him, Penny.
We'll give you anything you want.
Anything?
Okay, then. I won't tell him,
on one condition:
I want that treasure.
[gasps]
[sighs]
[groans]
I can't believe you agreed to this.
She can't be trusted. She's a… Peabody.
I know, but we have to save the museum.
This is our only option.
Sometimes a commander's
got to make tough calls.
-You're doing the right thing.
-I really hope so.
This museum is way too special
to let the Peabodys ruin it.
[butterflies giggling]
[whale] Oh, yeah.
It feels so good
to shake my tail after a long day.
Whoa.
If my treasure map-reading skills
are as bodacious as my tail,
I'm pretty sure we go… hm, hm, hm,
down there.
-Ugh.
-But my couture wraps are dry-clean only.
[laughs]
Oh, I thought that was a joke.
I don't joke about couture.
Okay, team, let's go find that treasure.
[grunting]
-Do you need help, Penny?
-Me? No.
Never. A Peabody can figure out
anything on their own.
[grunting]
Okay, well, see you at the bottom.
Why couldn't our 100th adventure
be somewhere warm and cozy and safe?
Like a tropical beach
with fruity drinks and tiny umbrellas.
Don't worry, Dudley.
Just stay calm
and we'll touch down in no time.
It's so dark down here,
I can't see my hooves.
Here, Fred. Let me.
I've been known to light up a room.
My hooves! Thanks, Princess.
[grunts, screams]
Whoa!
Penny, are you okay?
That was awesome!
[clears throat]
I mean, awesomely dangerous.
My uncle would shut this place down
immediately if he knew about it.
I wish I didn't know about it.
This place is terrifying.
We've been on 99 other adventures.
As long as we're together, we've got this.
-Dante, lead the way.
-Sure thing, dudette.
Let's kick it.
So, you're an astronaut?
You betcha. First monkey to slip
on a banana peel in space.
No monkeying around with the enemy,
Peaches.
Mind your own beeswax, pigeon.
Ah! I'm a dodo bird, for your information.
And I'm the last of my kind.
This museum is the only home I have left.
[whimpers]
Is that true?
We're all family here.
The museum's our home.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Yo, I think we're almost there.
Wonder what these spiky things are?
Oh, got it.
Super pointy death traps. Gnarly.
Hoof it or lose it!
-Go!
-Run!
[shudders]
-Whoa!
-Ridley!
Gotcha.
Penny, come on. It's not safe.
[panting]
Oh! She's not gonna make it!
I can't look!
Slide, Penny!
[grunts]
-Bisonic stampeding.
-That was close.
I can't believe I just did that.
Coolest moment of my life.
Whoa.
Dude, we did it.
Even holding the map
upside down the whole time.
Wait, don't touch.
With this, my uncle will finally be able
to take over the museum
and sell everything.
What?
I told you a Peabody couldn't be trusted.
Every artifact.
Every painting. All of you.
[Ridley] No!
-[screams]
-[grunts] Mummazing catch.
-Bisonic move.
[grunts, screams]
[grunts] I got you, Penny.
Oh no, it's slipping.
Come on, grab the rope.
But she's going to help
her uncle sell our home.
That doesn't matter now.
It's my job to protect everything
and everybody in this museum,
including Penny.
It's the right thing to do.
-Totally.
-Hang in there!
[all grunting]
Stay calm, Penny. We got you.
It's not enough.
Even with my bison strength.
Dudley, we need you.
[Penny] Please, Dudley, I need you.
[whimpers] Okay.
[all grunting]
-Ah!
-[Ridley] Got you.
I can't believe you saved me.
That's what we do.
We look out for each other.
Yeah, I noticed that. This place isn't
at all what I thought it was.
You've made me realize I was wrong
about a lot of things, actually.
♪ I trusted our old family motto ♪
♪ My uncle's selfish golden rule ♪
♪ It's you for you, forget the others ♪
♪ I guess I've been a selfish fool ♪
♪ But now I see
That I've been mistaken ♪
♪ Now I see what I need to do ♪
♪ Now I see the lesson I've taken ♪
♪ It's you for me and me for you ♪
♪ I'll learn to live
With more compassion ♪
♪ I'll think about how others feel ♪
♪ I'll trust that
When we trust each other ♪
♪ That's when the world is most ideal ♪
♪ Oh, now I see I've been misdirected ♪
♪ Now I see with a new worldview ♪
♪ Now I see that we're all connected ♪
♪ It's you for me ♪
♪ And me for you ♪
[sighs] I'm really sorry
about how I acted earlier.
And don't worry,
I won't tell my uncle anything.
Your secret is safe with me. I promise.
-How queenly of you.
-Yes!
Thank you, Penny.
Here. A deal's a deal.
No. That treasure belongs here,
where it'll be protected.
Under one condition.
[all] Huh?
Can I come hang out
with you guys sometime?
Absolutely.
-You bet.
-Yeah.
Turns out I kind of like you.
I guess I can make an exception
to my never-trust-a-Peabody rule. [laughs]
I couldn't think of a better way
to celebrate my 100th.
We worked as a team, found
a hidden treasure, and made a new friend.
I couldn't think of a better way
to celebrate my first.
I fell down a well, ran through
a booby-trapped cave, made 6 new friends.
-[Peabody] Niece?
-Mr. Peabody! Hide!
Ah, there you are. You missed out
on a lively night of counting.
[chuckles]
I'm sure. Come on.
I think it's time for us to go home.
So? What did you find out?
Sorry, Uncle. There's nothing to report.
This is just a regular, boring old museum.
-I'm ready for my 100th stamp.
-[Mama] I'm so proud of you, sweetie.
And for your 100th mission,
you don't just get a stamp.
Now that you're a stronger protector,
you're ready for…
Wow. What does it do?
This is a Hero's Hand.
Every skilled protector has one.
There are tools inside it that'll
help you get through all kinds of jams.
I want to try.
Whoa! [chuckles]
Thanks, Mama.
I promise to use
the Hero's Hand with pride.
Now let's try this one.
-Whoa!
-[laughs]
[theme song plays]