♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive ♪
♪ She is saving our future
By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear ♪
♪ She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
[Ridley] Flight School Dropout.
-[Ridley] You got this!
-[cheering]
-[Dante] Whoa!
Splendid form, Perry.
And now our final flier: Dudley.
Thanks, everyone.
I hope you're floored by my routine.
[chuckles]
Get it? 'Cause I'm on the floor.
'Cause I can't fly yet.
But I've always wanted
to be in a flying recital.
So, well… [squeaks]
Dudley? Are you feeling okay?
I'm feeling like a dodo
about to embarrass himself.
I can't fly like Perry.
But you can perform like Dudley.
Trust me, you can do this.
You've practiced and practiced,
and now you just got to go for it.
Thanks, Ridley. Okay. Here goes.
And one and two and, uh, hi, hi.
Whoo and whee!
Buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh!
Love a routine with flair.
Hip. Hi!
[laughs]
Ah!
[grunts]
[cheering]
Uh-oh.
The Wall of Wind.
Oh, remember, hon.
Don't fight the wind. Waltz with it.
Yes. Now ride the breeze.
[shudders] Waltz with the wind.
[chuckles]
Ha!
Whee!
Whoo-hoo!
-Amazing!
-Go, Dudley!
You like the twirls? Really?
Even though I didn't technically…
Fly? Oh, you bet.
[snorts] I might add
a twirl to my next stampede.
-[bird] Incoming!
-Hey!
[laughs]
Whoa! [grunts]
Brace for impact!
-[Dudley] Ah!
-[all scream]
[laughs]
Hey, it's the dodo with the dance moves.
-I'm Stella.
-Hi.
Are you two okay?
Ah, sure. You can't fly like the wind
without bonking
off a few walls, right, Dodo?
-Uh…
-Your speed is incredible,
but your landings
are a little on the messy side.
Oh, guess so.
Oh, this ruby has a crack.
Mr. Peabody
is not gonna be stoked if he notices.
Oh, I have an idea.
You all know
about the Vermilion Star, right?
Nope.
Hm. Might be a royalty thing.
Anyhoo, it's a giant ruby that was lost
in the Arctic a gazillion dynasties ago.
If we find it and bring it to the museum,
Peabody won't notice anything else.
Got to say, that just might work.
Ismat, let's make a plan.
Everyone else,
get ready for an Arctic ruby rescue.
If getting ready means
worrying about frostbite, I'm on it.
Oh! Hear me out.
You can skip worrying
and come be my wingman.
[grunts]
[chuckles] You want to hang out with me?
Sure, she does, Dudley.
You are the chillest bird around.
Just go for it, remember? Have fun.
See? I knew you were cool.
Oh, Ridley was just being nice.
I'm as cool as a fleece-lined sweater
with a heater inside.
[gasps] But maybe if I practiced.
Say, do you give coolness lessons?
Sure. Lesson number one:
lessons aren't cool.
And anyway, you don't need them, Dodo.
♪ You can be cool
Don't even sweat it ♪
♪ All that it takes is a brand-new style ♪
♪ Lessons or class?
Baby, forget it ♪
♪ Just be a little less you
For a little while ♪
♪ You'll be cool
Just soar through the air ♪
♪ Relaxed, debonair, carefree ♪
♪ So cool ♪
♪ With just an adjustment or three ♪
♪ You'll be cool like me ♪
♪ Show me your strut
Give it some bluster ♪
♪ Act like it's swagger that you exude ♪
♪ Add some panache
All you can muster ♪
♪ Try a new look
With a bit more attitude ♪
♪ You'll be cool ♪
♪ All chill and aloof ♪
♪ Anxiety-proof, you'll see ♪
♪ So cool ♪
♪ Just trust me and I guarantee ♪
♪ You'll be cool like me ♪
♪ Cool like me ♪
[grunting]
Thanks, Mr. Bird, sir.
Abso-dodo-lutely.
Looking to make that banana split?
[both gasp]
-Flashlight?
-Check.
-Map to the Vermilion Star?
Is that Dudely? [chuckles]
Love the new look.
But you'll need a warmer coat.
[panting] Bad news, team.
Cameras are showing
a storm brewing in the Arctic.
Oh no!
Well, it's not worth risking
life and wing, or hoof and tail.
We better wait for the storm to pass.
Oh, rescue rain check. Bummer.
Cheer up, Eyes.
The time will fly by if we spend it
sledding in the tundra exhibit.
-Yes!
-I mean, we are dressed for snow.
[all exclaim]
Oh, I wanted to show everyone
how cool I could be on a mission.
Yo, Dodo, you heading out
to find that Ruby? Sounds fun.
Hey, hey, hey! Hold on!
Peaches just warned us
there's a dangerous storm coming.
Oh, Dodo, the whole point of being cool
is you don't listen to warnings
if they ruin the fun.
You want to have fun, don't you?
Why, I believe I, uh, dodo-do.
Fun, right?
Who needs warnings
and training and mittens?
Oops, forgot my mittens.
Ooh, but still, this is cool.
Also, very cold.
But more importantly, cool.
The faster you go, the warmer you'll get.
-Ah! Oh!
-Whoa!
[grunts]
Hey, I just stumbled
beak over tail feathers, and I feel great.
[laughs] Told you.
Leap before you look, I always say.
Hm. Leap before you look. Got it.
[Stella] Whee!
[laughing]
Oh, check it.
Ooh! The Vermilion Star. It's so big.
[grunts]
Mr. Peabody will be distracted for months.
I can't wait to show Ridley.
I think I'm finally getting
the hang of that sledding business.
Ridley! Dudley didn't show up
for his six o'clock wing stretches.
It's un-bird of.
That doesn't sound like Dudely.
Where do you think he is?
Well, the last time we saw him was right
before the mission at the Arctic exhibit.
[gasps] Oh no!
I bet he went after the ruby on his own.
I kept telling him to just go for it.
I didn't mean
just go into a giant blizzard.
We got to find him
before the storm hits.
Come on.
No need to panic. Totally cool.
We'll just leap before we look. [chuckles]
'Cause we can't see
anything anyway, right?
[squeals]
[grunts]
-Nice and slow.
-What?
I said we should go slow!
Yeah, this is too slow.
No! Wait!
We'll be home in no time, Dodo!
Whoa!
Oh, feathers.
Whoa! [grunts]
[wind howling]
Stella!
Oh, Stella, you're alive.
Come on out. Get out of the snow.
I can't. Uh…
My wings are frozen stiff.
Uh, I'm on my way.
[grunts] I just need to leap before I--
Ah! Ah! [shivers]
Leap before I-- [grunts]
It's like the Wall of Wind,
but bigger and colder
and impossible to get through.
I shouldn't have flown in here.
Now I can't fly us out.
[grunts] Hey, I flew in here too,
in a walking kind of way.
[sighs] If only Ridley knew we were here.
-[Peaches] Give a holler, Sunshine!
-[Ridley] Can you hear us?
We've got a lot of ground to cover.
We should spread out.
Leaping lunar modules.
This is like wandering
through a cloud of stardust.
I could barely see you.
Good point, Peaches.
We could lose each other.
Stay close, everyone.
Oh, I wish we could let
our Dodo bro know we're out here.
Wait. We can.
We can't see Dudley,
but maybe Dudley can see this.
The last thing I'll ever see
before I turn into a Popsicle.
[sobs]
A signal flare.
Ay! A signal flare?
It's Ridley!
Stella, the Eyes are coming,
and if they can fight
through a blizzard to save me,
I can waltz with the wind to save you.
Yeah, I hear you, wind,
and I have just one question.
May I have this dance?
Uh…
[humming]
Gotcha! [grunts]
Dodo!
We're almost there, Stella.
Waltz with me. Hm?
[humming]
Oh! There they are.
You can fly straight to them.
But how? My wings don't work.
Sure, they do.
See, a very cool eagle
once taught me, "Ride the breeze."
[both] Whoo-hoo!
[both laugh]
Hey, look at us! We're flying! Uh…
Poor Dudley. He must be so scared.
Maybe aim for that sparkly
and oddly fashion-forward cloud.
That's no cloud.
It's Dudley.
[both screaming]
-[grunts]
-Dudley.
-Ridley, I'm sorry I--
-You're okay.
[chuckles] Yeah.
Let's hug it out before I explain.
Well, you did it,
but you almost got lost forever.
And that's as close to extinction
as this dodo ever wants to go.
No more leaping before looking for me.
That's the way I like it.
We're just glad you're back, Sunshine.
And I'm just glad
you were there to save me.
You're the bravest dodo I know.
[snorts and laughs]
He's the only dodo you know.
[chuckles] But, like, we get it.
Well, I'd love to stay and chat,
but I've got a flying lesson to catch.
[laughs] Time to ride the breeze.
Hey, uh, can I come?
I mean, since all the coolest birds
are dodo doing it.
Abso-dodo-lutely.
[all laugh]
[Fred] Oh, Dudley.
[theme music plays]