♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive ♪
♪ She is saving our future
By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear ♪
♪ She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
[Ridley] Pedro Busts a Move.
Help! Please help me!
[Peaches] Ten-four, little buddy!
I found Pedro, but I can't land
on that ice floe without tipping it over.
We need to move fast.
Thanks to Captain Finn,
I've got just what I need.
Turn hard to starboard, first mate Dante.
Wait, is starboard
Ralph's left or Ralph's right?
-Right.
-Uh, and is my tail's right my right?
-Go that way.
-Aye, aye, Captain Dudette.
We'll take it from here, Peaches.
Now let's go save Pedro.
-Aye, matey.
-Argh!
[Ridley] Port. Starboard. Whoa, port!
-Whoa.
-That was a close one.
Oh right. My other starboard.
We've got one Pedro straight ahead.
[grunts]
Oh, hi, Ridley. Whoa!
-Oh dear!
-He's done for!
Don't worry, Pedro. I'll save you.
[grunts]
[Pedro] Whoo!
Gotcha.
-Go, Ridley!
-Wow. Jurassick.
I'm the queen of the world. Whoo-hoo-hoo!
A-plus captaining, Ridley.
And good thing
the museum gave us these tablets.
They make rescues
easy as banana cream pie.
I'll see you soon, my yummy friend. Mm.
Hey, Pedro. You okay, little buddy?
Yeah. I'm sorry I got stuck on the ice.
I tried to watch where I was going,
but I was feeling sad.
Don't be sad. I love rescuing you.
It's not that. I'm sad because I'm moving.
Moving? Well, that's okay.
Exhibits move
around the museum all the time.
Ooh, I hope
they move you to the second floor.
They just opened a gender-neutral
bathroom with high-powered hand driers,
and they're awesome.
I'm not sure
if I'm moving to the second floor.
Well, let's ask Mama Penguin.
She'll know exactly
where you're moving to.
This should be almost enough boxes
to move all of my snow globes.
-Oh hello, Ridley.
-Hey, Mama Penguin.
Pedro told us about your move,
and we're so happy.
-Can't wait.
-[laughs] Righteous.
Mama, where in the museum
are we moving to?
Oh, sorry, Pedro. We're not staying here.
We're moving
to a different museum across the country.
A different museum?
[gasps] Oh no!
But if you're gone, who will be
my favorite boogie board partner?
Who will make us snow cones?
Or frozen bananas.
I can't lose a fellow flightless bird.
What will I do without
the second-cutest critter in the museum?
As we all know, I am the first cutest.
And Pedro was my first rescue.
And my last rescue.
Who will rescue Pedro if I'm not there?
Yeah, who?
Oh baby, I'm sorry.
[cries]
Mama, can my friends come with me?
No, mijo. They have to stay here.
But your friend Mr. Fish
is coming along for the ride.
Now start packing your nest.
The moving truck should be here soon,
and we don't want to be late.
[sighs] I guess I'm really going.
Bye, Ridley.
Pedro, don't worry. We'll save you.
We never give up.
We have to find a way
to get Pedro to stay.
Now that you're all here…
Whoops. [chuckles]
…in our living room, what is this about?
Pedro. You can't let him move.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
That's just how traveling exhibits work.
Sometimes they have to move
so other people can enjoy them.
It's hard, but it's part of museum life.
[sighs] There must be something we can do.
The best thing you can do now
is help Pedro be ready for his move.
-[clattering]
-That must be the movers.
They probably didn't measure
the polar bear ice sculptures
before moving them. Gotta go.
It's okay, Sunshine. We tried.
We didn't try everything.
We've got to keep Pedro in the museum,
and I know just how to do it.
Listen up, Eyes. Here's the plan.
Ismat, you're with me on stickers.
Dante and Peaches, you're on glue duty.
Fred and Dudley, you're on decoy.
Everybody ready?
-Right.
-Roger that.
Operation Stop Pedro's Move is a go.
Eyes on three. One, two…
Eyes!
All the boxes with stickers on them
need to go in the moving truck.
[mysterious music plays]
Lift with your tiny arms, Dante.
Totes. [grunting]
They'll never be able to move this box
now that it's covered in glue.
Fred and Dudley, you're up.
And they'll think this is Pedro?
You bet your hoof they will. See?
[imitating Pedro]
Hey. It's me, Pedro. Really.
Oh, hi, Pedro, do you want to--
Wait a second.
It worked. I was totally fooled.
[laughs]
Told you. Take us home, Ismat and Ridley.
Piece of cake. Let's move in.
[humming]
Oh.
Huh? Uh, what?
Oh! Hey! Hey! Don't move me!
We did it, team.
Pedro is going to stay
in the museum forever.
-We rule!
-Totes.
Hey, this penguin is full of rocks.
[grunts]
We got it.
[blubbering]
[chuckles]
Sorry, I thought you were a box.
Would a box
have a gorgeous mustache like this?
Well, I guess
we celebrated a bit too soon.
It's okay.
The moving truck isn't here yet.
There's still time to…
-[vehicle approaching]
-[sighs] Never mind.
Hey, Ridley,
can I stay in the museum forever now?
[sighs] No. I'm so sorry, Pedro.
We tried, but there's nothing we could do.
You were my first rescue,
but I couldn't save you
this one last time, and…
Whoa. Normally bubble wrap is so fun,
but today it's mega sad.
We're never gonna see Pedro again. [cries]
But I don't want to go.
[cries]
I don't want you to go either.
Ridley, can we talk for a second?
I know this is hard,
but do you know who it's harder for?
Than me? No.
-I'm totally broken up over Pedro moving.
-[cries]
But… [sighs]
…so is Pedro.
That's right, and he has to face
being scared of going someplace new.
That's awful.
What he needs is his friends
to support him with his big move.
You're right, Mama.
And I know just what to do.
Mama Penguin said I'd be okay,
but I'm not okay, Mr. Fish.
They can't move us if they can't find us.
Pedro? We've got a surprise for you.
Oh, I worked my hooves off
to make the perfect goodbye cake
with delicious fish paste.
Oh, Pedro is going to love it.
Yeah, but where is the little guy?
Pedro? Pedro?
Ay, Pedro ran away.
All he left was this note.
"I don't want to move,
so I ran away
where no one would ever find me."
-[all gasp]
-Oh no.
If I didn't want anyone to find me,
I'd hide next to the feather duster
because we look like twins, see?
-Ah.
-I see it.
-Twinsies.
-Perfect resemblance.
I've saved Pedro enough times
to know where he's hiding.
The place where we had
our first adventure together.
The Serengeti. Come on.
-Whoo-hoo!
-Let's do this.
-Well, this looks familiar.
-[cries]
Stay still, Pedro.
We're gonna come save you.
No. If there's one thing
I've learned from today,
it's that me and Mr. Fish
need to save ourselves.
-It's the only way.
-[rumbling]
Whoa!
[screams]
Don't worry, Pedro. I've got you.
-[adventurous music plays]
-Ah!
-Ah.
-Huh.
Thanks for saving me, Ridley.
My pleasure.
Pedro, I'm sorry
for making you sad earlier.
I was so focused on my feelings
that I didn't stop
to think about how you feel.
I just want you to know
that I'm here for you, now and always.
-Really?
-Really.
We'll always be friends.
Moving can never change that.
We can write and call and visit.
I'd like that.
I'd like that, too.
No matter what happens,
we'll be friends wherever we are.
♪ You're off on a new adventure ♪
♪ And I know it may feel strange ♪
♪ But wherever you may travel ♪
♪ There are things that never change ♪
-♪ So move clear across the universe ♪
-[laughs]
♪ Our friendship can stretch that far ♪
♪ We'll be friends
No matter where you are ♪
♪ 'Cause friends
Will stay friends forever ♪
♪ Even though they're miles apart ♪
♪ Despite all the space between us ♪
♪ You'll be right here in my heart ♪
♪ So if you should move to Zambia ♪
♪ Zimbabwe, or Zanzibar ♪
♪ We'll be friends
No matter where you are ♪
Thanks, Ridley.
With you by my side, I can do anything.
Even move far, far away.
We're so excited
about your big move, Pedro.
You're gonna love it at your new museum.
I hear they just got a T. rex exhibit.
Me and Rexy go way back.
Tell her I said, "Sup."
Pedro, before you go,
I've got something special for you.
It's loaded up with the latest
Eyes of the Museum chat,
so you can talk to us whenever you want.
Wow! Thanks, Ridley.
And before I go, I want you to have this.
Mr. Fish? Really?
Really. If you ever need saving,
he'll be there for you. [chuckles]
I'll always remember you, friend.
[engine starts]
Come on, mijo. It's time to go.
Okay, Mama. Bye, everyone.
[sighs]
[chimes]
Hi, Ridley. Are you busy?
Uh, I'm a little busy. [chuckles]
But I always have time for you.
Good. I'm having so much fun
in my new museum. I even met the T. rex.
[T. rex roars]
Oh no. Do you need saving?
No, Rexy is nice. She's just really loud.
Anyway, my museum has lots of cool stuff,
like a lucha libre exhibit
and hoop dancers and a room full of cats
and a tank full of great chopper sharks.
Lots of cool stuff.
[chuckles]
[theme music plays]