♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive ♪
♪ She is saving our future
By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear
She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
[Ridley] Makin' Waves.
[Mama] Almost.
A little farther.
-There.
-And the hull's intact.
Shiver me timbers.
We'll finally have a pirate exhibit.
-Hey there.
-Ridley.
Ahoy, team. Welcome the Queen Barnacle
aboard to our museum.
-So cool.
-Fantastic.
Here's the last piece.
Secure the wheel when you're ready
for some museum magic.
I'm always ready for museum magic.
Thanks for helping me, team.
Our queenly pleasure, Ridley.
You know I love VIP access.
Oh, and I've been a mega pirate fan
for, like, 65 million years.
You do know pirates have only
been around for 3,000 years, right?
Yeah, dates aren't really my thing,
but I can talk like a pirate. Argh!
[chuckles]
That's pretty accurate. Here we go.
Argh!
[all cheer]
Ahoy, buccaneers. I'm Captain Finn.
And this here's my mighty pirate crew,
Chip and Tootles.
And that is my sword.
Welcome to the museum.
I'm Ridley, and this is the Eyes Team.
Hey, there.
I'm a huge fan of your work, pirate dudes.
-Totes inspirational.
-Ooh, and I celebrate your work as well.
Thanks for fixing the Queen B for me.
Oh, who put me in this frilly frock?
[grunts] Argh!
That's better.
I obviously love an outfit change,
but dare I say,
I love your fearlessness even more?
-Why, thank you, mate.
-Let's give you the grand tour.
Oh no. My hat. I can't do anything
until I find my captain's hat.
-We'll help you find it, Captain Finn.
-[Peabody] Argh! Yo-ho-ho.
-Museum Mayday!
-Scatter, dudes.
You got to stay still
when Mr. Peabody's around.
-What if I don't want to stay quiet?
-Please, Finn?
It's the only way to keep
the museum's secret secret.
Silent as the grave, me hearties.
Finally.
Something spectacular in this museum.
My mama and grandma sure did
a nice job restoring the ship, huh?
Did you know
it is my lifelong dream to be a pirate?
Ah! Oh! [clears throat]
Anyone who steals treasure and hoards it
for themself is a bona fide hero to me.
-Argh! Give me back me hat.
-Who said that?
Uh, hey, Mr. P,
isn't that the captain's hat?
I am the captain of the museum.
But the captain's hat belongs to--
The one who's the bravest
most manly man here, of course.
Ooh, look at this manly fellow.
He looks like the ship's leader.
And what is this woman doing here?
She can't be a part of my dream ship.
Ooh!
-I must get her off at once.
-Wait. No.
[panting]
-Put her in storage before we open.
-Mr. Peabody, she's the captain--
Ms. Jones, do not get in the way
of my favorite exhibit.
Not as long
as you value your family's jobs.
Argh! He's erasing me from history.
I would say you get used to him,
but you never really do.
That scallywag should walk the plank.
Everyone knows
I'm the captain of this vessel.
Aye-aye, Captain Finn here
is the fiercest commander to boot.
She sails the toughest seas.
Discovers the shiniest treasures.
And even gives me ginger ale
when me tummy gets the sea bubbles.
Precisely. No one can ignore me.
You know, Finn, you seem rad,
but I've seen lots of pictures of pirates,
and I've never seen a lady pirate.
Just saying.
Well, you're seeing one now.
Well, sure, but, like,
you've never been in my pirate books.
-Hold this, you parrot.
-[stutters] Okay.
That doesn't mean we don't exist.
Hear, hear.
What do you reckon we do about Peabody
wanting to put you in storage?
Storage? Argh!
I refuse to have such a fate.
In fact,
I'm starting my own crew somewhere else.
Which way to the nearest shore?
Captain Finn, come back.
You forgot this!
[pants] Oof!
[grunts] Now I have the sea bubbles!
[Dante] Hey, mighty pirate dudes.
How about we brave the waves
and take this out for a spin?
Captain Finn's decides
when we venture out to sea.
Though I guess someone has to take over.
-Huh. Well, you have the hat.
-Aye.
Does that mean I'm the captain now?
Hm. Very well then.
Tootles, sail the, uh… sail.
Righteous.
I got a list of questions for you.
Firstly, where do you get snacks at sea?
How many swords
can you hold at the same time?
Oh, are dolphins total party animals?
'Cause that's what I've heard.
Listen up, me hearties.
If I can no longer be the captain
of me old crew, I'll be yours.
Now, let's start with pirate basics.
Give me your best "yo-ho-ho."
Yo-ho-ho!
What Mr. Peabody did was totally unfair,
so we're happy to join your new crew.
Aye. Now, pirates need to be tough
at all times, like this.
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
See what I did there?
Now let's see
your mighty strong pirate stance.
[all] Argh!
You'll be A-plus pirates in no time.
I'm glad you're here
to listen to my captain ways.
[sighs] I do miss my Queen B, though.
Then let's blast on over to her.
I got a hankering for sailing.
Peaches, you and I see eye to eye.
She is my ship, after all.
Let's go, mateys.
[gasps] Queen Barnacle! My vessel!
-Oh no.
-Queen B!
Houston, we have a pirate problem.
[gasps] Dante's aboard.
There's no captain.
We gotta catch up before someone
gets hurt. Know of any other ships?
Ships? No.
But I know the best whale
to sail the seven seas.
Whee! Hold on.
It's gonna be a bumpy ride.
-Whoo-hoo!
-[laughing]
Do the wave!
Ah! I would, but I'm gonna need
both wings to hold on for dear life!
There's Queen B! Blimey.
A storm is heading our way.
You sure about that, Captain Finn?
This is us, lass.
We need some turbo-mega-super speed.
You betcha.
Oh, why do you have
to make everything so scary?
No, I have to make
everything an adventure!
-Whoo-hoo!
-[Dudley screams]
Now for question number 410.
Whoa!
[Dante screams]
Easy, ship. You're totally buggin'.
So, like, what do we do
about these mondo rocky waves?
Aye.
Uh, that's a question for Captain Finn.
-[thunder crashes]
-Whoa!
Oh! Anchors aweigh. Like, literally.
Thanks, Mrs. Sanchez. We got it from here.
Yo-ho-ho and a bottle of krill.
Whoa. Hey, dudes.
How'd you get here so quick?
A captain knows how to lead her crew.
Ahoy, Finn. What a relief to see you.
Aye. Time to focus, crew.
-Uh-oh.
-Yo-ho-no!
We got to sail out of here
before we hit the eye of the storm.
Uh-um, matey?
Right! Here you go, Finn. [chuckles]
That's Captain Finn to you.
[grunts] The ship's stuck.
[all scream]
Now we've really hit rock bottom.
No need to fret.
[grunts] I have a plan.
Be my right-hand matey?
Absolutely. Argh!
We'll need to get to the crow's nest
for a bird's-eye view of the problem.
Follow my lead.
[grunts]
Looks like the anchor
is stuck under a rock.
All hands on deck!
Chip, Tootles, steady the sail.
The rest of you, grab that rope and pull.
Aye-aye, Captain Finn.
Alrighty. On three. One, two, three.
[grunting]
Pull, mateys. Keep at it. Almost there.
[all screaming]
Well done, crew. We did it.
I was totally wrong.
Lady dudes can do anything.
Sorry I doubted you.
You have the coolest moves,
O captain, my captain.
Apology accepted, mate.
Just 'cause we're not in books,
doesn't mean we don't exist.
And I got my mighty
captain's hat after all, right?
Totes. You know, it turns out
you can be millions of years old
and still have stuff to learn.
[laughs]
Absolutely.
♪ There are stories to tell
That have never been told ♪
♪ Though they ought to be spread
Near and far ♪
♪ When they're writing their books
We get left in the cold ♪
♪ Just because of the pirates we are ♪
♪ True the seas may be rough
But we're weathered and tough ♪
♪ As we wait for that wonderful day ♪
♪ When we're given our due
Like the rest of the crew ♪
♪ But I fear that day's oceans away ♪
♪ We're explorers and leaders
Who all have been robbed ♪
♪ We contributed more than you know ♪
♪ But the decks of our history
All have been swabbed ♪
♪ And our treasures are buried below ♪
♪ We've got leagues yet to sail ♪
♪ But if you tell our tale ♪
♪ Then this captain can finally say ♪
♪ That the yarn shall be spun
Of the deeds that I've done ♪
♪ May that day not be oceans ♪
♪ Away ♪
Almost home.
If I could just figure out
a way to fix my exhibit.
You know,
this whole adventure inspired me.
I challenge you to a duel, Ridley.
Have at me, Captain Finn.
-[both] Ha!
-Ha-ha!
Huh!
-Ah!
-Ha-ha!
-[grunting]
-[cheering]
No one told me about a pirate show.
-Wow!
-Go, Ridley!
[grunting]
I love it!
[grunts]
-Take that!
-[grunts]
Argh! You beat me again.
Captain Finn is clearly
the champion of the sea.
[cheering]
-Yeah, Captain Finn!
-Go!
-Go, Ridley! You're the best!
-Amazing!
That was incredible! Yo-ho-ho!
You're the best shipmate
a pirate could ask for, but watch out.
[grunting]
Ahoy, Finn.
Okay, yeah.
[laughing]
[theme song plays]