♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive ♪
♪ She is saving our future
By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear
She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
[Ridley] Lonny's Ready.
Lion manes combed, beach combed,
comb exhibit combed.
-What's next on our evening checklist?
-Ooh. Hey there, Eyes Team.
Having museum fun, as per usual?
-Affirmative.
-You know it.
I don't know if you know,
but ever since I found out
about you guys being alive and all,
I've been dying to go
on a bona fide Eyes Team adventure.
[chuckles] That floor's already shiny
as a buttered biscuit, Sunshine.
[chuckles] Oh. Right.
I guess I'm done for the night.
I, uh, should get going.
Unless…
Do you think
your old pal Lonny could tag along?
I'm jonesing for a mission,
pun practiced and very much intended.
Oh, um, we don't really
have a mission planned for tonight.
-We're just making our museum rounds.
-I don't mind. I just want to hang.
Pretty please
with priceless artifacts on top?
Uh…
-Yeah, sure.
-[all gasp]
Yippee! Yip, yip, yip, yippee!
♪ I know in my heart I'm ready ♪
Sorry. My bad.
Are we sure this is a good idea?
I'm not sure Lonny
is exactly cut out for Eyes Team action.
I know what you mean,
but it's been a quiet night so far
and we're just going through
the cleanup checklist.
I love a safe, predictable checklist.
It's check-bliss.
Sounds pretty Lonny-proof to me.
Come on, got to document
my first night on the team.
Say, "Eyes."
[all] Oh! Eyes?
Do I still have eyes?
[grunting]
Bringing dinner to the avian wing
is my favorite stop on the checklist.
Mm.
It's din-din time, little bird dudes.
Who's hungry?
Oh, hiya. I don't think we've met.
I'm Ridley, and this is the Eyes Team.
-What up?
-Charmed.
Nice to meet you. I'm Bill.
Oh, and thanks for the grub.
This bowerbird loves bowerbird-seed.
Mm!
Huh? That looks just like
my missing belt buckle.
What a coincidence.
You got great taste, my friend. [chuckles]
If only I could find that thing.
-[all gasp]
-Whoa!
-[grunting]
-[birds squawking]
[chuckles]
Birds fed, caribou herded, whale flossed.
[sighs] Looks like we're all done here.
-Ismat!
-Ismy!
-Dads? What's wrong?
-Your crown sapphire. It's… [gasps]
…missing.
But it's been in our family
for generations.
And it looks good with my eyes.
[chuckles]
We've got to find it.
Well, seems like we'll have
a classic Eyes mission tonight after all.
Yippee! Let me just put
my cleaning supplies away first.
Wait, we're not letting Lonny
join us for a real mission, right?
Well, we did promise
she could tag along tonight.
-Ridley's got a point, y'all.
-We'd be totes rude to tell her no.
Exactly. And I'm sure
Lonny's gotten the hang of things by now.
[Lonny grunts]
[groans]
Be right there! [chuckles]
So this is the last place
you saw the sapphire?
Yup. Right here.
Okay, Eyes. Let's dust for prints.
Hey, gang, take a look at this.
I think it's birdseed.
-[Ridley] Hm.
-Ah!
-[sneezes]
-[all cough]
-O-M-Ra!
-[Lonny] Sorry, pals.
[laughs] Good thing this is the Eyes Team
and not the Nose Team, am I right?
-[laughs]
-Um, Ridley, a word?
[sighs] It pains me to say,
Fred was right.
I don't think Lonny is ready for this.
This isn't any old life-or-death mission.
This is about jewelry. My jewelry.
Everyone makes mistakes, Ismat.
You know, I think I'm gonna
mosey on over to the security room.
Great idea, Peaches.
We can check
the security footage for clues.
Oh, that's my office. I'll go, too.
[chuckles]
[snorts]
Okay, if we wait one more second,
we'll see the culprit right…
here.
Lonny, I think you just
erased the footage.
Oh, pickles. I'm sorry, Peaches.
[sighs] That's all right.
Ah! Oop! Sorry again.
[sighs] This time you've gone too far!
It's okay, Lonny.
I saw Ma and Pa
before the footage was erased.
-Let's start by talking to them.
-Wah-hoo! We have a lead.
[horses neigh]
Come on, team.
Ma, run!
Bandits!
-Well, that's not suspicious at all.
-I command you to stop!
Eat my dust, thieves! [chuckles]
We got to go after them.
[Ma] They're gaining on us, Pa!
-Hi-yah!
-[grunts]
[grunts]
-Got you.
-[horses neigh]
Ma, Pa, it's time for you
to return Ismat's crown sapphire.
-Her whosie-what now?
-My crown sapphire. In your wagon.
We didn't take no sapphire.
You didn't?
Why did you run
when you saw us coming?
You were trying to steal our loot.
We found this grahammy cracker feast.
You can't be too careful.
There's thieves around here.
Our favorite shiny bottle cap is missing.
Missing, you say?
Can you describe the missing item?
Uh, bottle cap. Blue. Shiny.
Real shiny.
Shiny, blue. Go on.
[groans] This is a dead end.
Let's move on, folks.
Did you say your stuff is missing?
Because I'm missing something too.
Interesting.
I lost my marbles.
Huh. You're not the only one, kiddo.
Where did you last have them, Pedro?
When I was playing
in the alpine exhibit…
Right here.
I put them down to make a snowman,
and then they were gone.
[chuckles] Well, aren't you handsome.
-[rumbling]
-Ah! What was that?
Uh-oh. No one make
any sudden movements or loud noises, okay?
-It might trigger--
-Look here!
A clue! Look!
[echoing] Look!
-[rumbling]
-[gasps]
Avalanche!
[grunts]
Let's hoof it out of here.
[screaming]
Everyone, hold on.
[groans]
I think I speak for everyone
when I say Lonny's got to go.
-It's not a good fit.
-Truth.
That woman is clumsier
than a mule in roller skates.
I'm not saying I told you so,
but I told you so.
I know. Look, you're right.
Lonny has been making
some pretty big mistakes.
[gasps]
And obviously, having her around
makes things a lot harder.
-Uh-huh.
-For sure.
[sniffles]
But we all made mistakes
when we first became a team.
We need to be more patient with Lonny.
♪ Lonny's not perfect
But neither are we ♪
♪ We've flubbed a thing or two
And some of us three ♪
♪ Nobody's perfect
Keep that in mind ♪
So be patient and kind ♪
♪ Peaches' banana peels
Or Dante, your tail ♪
♪ Like Dudley's fear of failure
They've made us fail ♪
♪ Nobody's perfect
That's how we live ♪
So we try to forgive ♪
♪ Through all our blunders
Our worst faux pas ♪
♪ We learn to love each other's flaws ♪
♪ Nobody's perfect ♪
♪ For heaven's sake ♪
♪ Nobody's perfect
We've all made a mistake ♪
♪ Nobody's perfect ♪
♪ Let's give Lonny a break ♪
I guess I used to be a little queenly.
Ralph had some trouble
adjusting to the team too.
Maybe there's a chance
I wasn't always so great
at admitting when I might not
be totally right.
Huh?
Oh.
We have to go talk to Lonny.
Hi, Lonny.
Hey.
We wanted to apologize
for being so impatient.
Because we realized
we need to be better teammates.
Nah, it's okay.
I heard what you said about me,
and it's true. [sighs]
I'm not cut out to be on the team.
-Oof. I guess I won't be needing this.
-Wait. Lonny, what is that?
Oh, this? That's my clue board.
I'd been collecting clues
and putting them on here.
You see,
between the birdseed and the feather,
I got to thinking
the perp's probably a bird.
I noticed the things that went missing,
and they're all shiny.
So I asked myself,
"Lonny, what bird likes shiny things?"
Then I answered myself,
"Well, Lonny, that'd be the bowerbird."
And Bill's exhibit says
they like to decorate with shiny objects.
Lonny, you cracked the case!
I know, I really messed it up.
Wait, do you mean I solved it?
You sure did. To the avian wing.
I know a shortcut.
Hey, Bill. We're missing some stuff.
-Think we could take a peek at your nest?
-Oh, sure! It's sort of messy, but…
My crown sapphire!
That's yours? I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to take people's stuff.
Please, take it all back.
Oh, so shiny.
[both grunting]
-Uh, Bill?
-Oh, right. [chuckles]
Sorry.
[grunts] Aha!
I just love, love, love shiny things.
I go all gaga-bird-brained
when I see something shiny.
Hm. Shiny, huh?
[gasps] Oh, I love, love, love it.
Thank you.
All right! [chuckles]
Lonny, your queen thanks you
for finding the royal crown sapphire.
You're a righteous teammate.
And we'd love it
if you joined the Eyes Team officially.
Oh, thanks, pals. I'd love to.
I'll be on every mission,
except when I'm working,
which is weeknights
and sometimes weekends.
-But not holidays. Except I'm not here--
-So… I guess you wouldn't want this then?
[gasps] My very own Eyes Team bandana?
Ooh!
Yay! [chuckles]
I think this calls for another
Eyes Team photo.
What do you say, Lon?
I'd say, "Eyes on three?"
One, two, Eyes!
[theme music plays]