♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive ♪
♪ She is saving our future
By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear
She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
[Ridley] Ismat's Cat-tastrophe.
I love how these boots look, but they…
Whoa!
-…aren't made for adventuring.
-I got you, Ridley.
Luckily, the runway won't be snowy.
Wait, maybe we should add snow.
It's so awesome of your dads
to include us in their fashion show.
Well, with a theme like Fashion Emergency,
of course our team needs
to be the stars of the runway.
Okay, team, show me what you got.
[dance music plays]
Is everyone runway-ready?
-Totally.
-Affirmative.
But isn't the runway indoors?
I'm freezing my tuchus off here.
It is, but I wanted
to test out our gear in the field.
This is the first time
my dads have invited me
to be a part of their big show,
and I can't let them down.
Speaking of down, are these pants
supposed to… [laughs]
…keep falling down?
Fashion isn't about
being functional, dude.
You look dodo chic, Dudley.
That's what matters.
Chic, huh? Then I'm on board--
Whoa! [screams]
Got you, Sunshine.
-[dad] Is that the sweetest little queen?
-Huh! Dads. Always giving me praise.
Hi, Dads. We're in the throne room.
[gasps] What?
-Whoa!
-[gasps]
[gasps]
What in the galaxy was that?
An intruder.
-Definitely a ghost.
-[gasps]
-I'll check it out.
-Careful.
Even the gentlest ghosts show no mercy.
-Aw! It's a kitten.
-[meows]
[chuckles]
-Cool.
-Whoa!
Oh, a sweet itty-bitty kitten. Ooh!
Don't even say it.
I am not being adorable.
-[chuckles]
-Hey, little dude.
She's still technically an intruder.
-[meows]
-Wowie. She loves my lights.
Oh, there she is.
She's quite the sprinter.
Dads, what's going on?
We are pleased to introduce
the newest member of our family,
Cleopatra Nebit Zahra the Cat.
-"Cleo" for short.
-[meows]
I wanted to call her Cleo-catra,
but that got vetoed by your dad.
[chuckles] Nice to meet you, Cleo.
Cats… [sneezes]
…start up my allergies,
but it's so worth it.
She's as sweet as banana pudding pie.
-And she has the softest fur.
-[purrs]
Sure, she's cute,
but we have a fashion show
to prepare for, right?
Right, Dads?
-[meows]
-Dads?
Isn't it time
for our mid-afternoon grape platter?
And where's my dancing peacocks?
Dads?
Hm? Oh, Ismat.
Didn't you say you wanted
more normalcy at home?
Less doting. Less gloating.
I guess. But I didn't mean this normal.
Hey, Ismat. Is everything okay?
Absolutely.
I just want my grapes
and peacocks and, you know,
just the usual attention
I get from my dads.
This cat is cramping my style.
But it's not like I'm jealous or anything.
Fine. I'm jealous, okay?
It's just, I'm so used
to being the center of my dads' world.
I don't like seeing them
pouring all their love over someone else.
That doesn't change
how much they love you.
-[laughing]
-[purrs]
I hope so.
[dance music plays]
[dad] Iconic.
Or as Fred would say, bisonic.
Ismat, you're up.
[meows]
[gasps]
Why is Cleo attending dress rehearsal?
This is a closed set.
We didn't want to leave her alone.
Did we, Cleo-leo-weo?
Now that's a catwalk.
[gasps]
Hey, you should put Cleo in the show.
-[both gasp]
-A guest star spot.
I love that.
Oh, we could put her in a caftan.
Or a cat-tan.
-[both laugh]
-Get it?
-But, Dads--
-To the costume wing.
Keep an eye on Cleo. We'll see you soon.
-[meows]
-Oh, fine.
But I'm not giving her
star treatment or anything.
This isn't for you.
[meows]
Huh! Cleo…
-[tearing]
-[gasps] Stop ruining everything!
-[meows]
-Go away, Cleo!
[meows]
Hey, Ismat.
-Where'd Cleo go?
-She ran off.
-[all gasp]
-No way!
But she'll be fine.
She has claws and everything. Believe me.
-We still have to find her.
-She's being a drama kitty.
As opposed to being a drama mummy queen?
If we start now,
we'll find her in no time.
-Who's with me?
-[all overlapping]
I'm gonna stay here.
I've got more important things to do,
like practice my twirl. [chuckles]
Okay, we should split up
to cover more ground. Let's go.
-You got it.
-Good thinking.
Mama Penguin said she heard meowing
coming from the Alpine exhibit.
-Cleo! You here?
-Dudette!
Dante! She went this way!
Gnarly. Let me go for a spin.
Righteous.
Found her!
-Hey, kitty cat. Come here.
-[meows]
Got you.
[sneezes]
Din-allergies. Come… [sneezes]
…back!
[sneezes] Oh!
[beeping]
Beans on a biscuit,
there's a cat in space!
How’d you get that helmet anyway?
Oh no. [grunts]
[Peaches chatters]
Oh my stars. Come back, kitty cat!
That's a no on the cello.
-She's not a drum fan either.
-[meows]
[meowing]
There you are, itty-bitty furball.
Whoa. [grunts]
That cat really
doesn't like your piano skills, Fred.
Everyone's a critic.
I was so close to catching that darn cat.
Me… [sneezes] …too.
Me three.
And now she could be anywhere.
Looking for a cat?
She ran thataway not too long ago.
Thanks, Mrs. S. Oh, and cool hat.
Gotta look my beluga best for tonight.
Did you check her throne? Sarcophagus?
Her bedazzled pyramid?
I did. I'm afraid Ridley was right.
Cleo's officially missing.
-It's okay to cry it out.
-I know.
[sobs]
[sighs]
Dads, I didn't mean to make you upset.
I got to find that cat,
even if it means she'll replace me.
[meowing]
Cleo. Finally, I found you.
This is not the best place
for a runaway kitten.
Ismat, you're here.
-I'm sorry it took me this long.
-It's okay. You're here now.
Right. Let's find Cleo.
[meows]
Hi, Cleo. Ooh!
Bye, Cleo.
Oh! Uh! Oh!
[groans]
Fashion is so hard to keep up with.
Literally.
-[meows]
-Ridley, she's heading your way!
[grunts]
I wish I had my rocket.
All I have is a spacesuit that lights up.
[gasps] That's it!
Peaches, turn on your spacesuit lights.
Uh, I don't know
if now's the best time to look fabulous.
It's for Cleo. She loves your lights.
Genius. Peaches, turn on your lights
and stand closer to Cleo.
Roger that.
-[suit beeping]
-[meows]
It's working.
Dudley, I'm gonna need those pants.
Gladly. Wait, they're still missing.
I've got this.
Yes!
Stay still, little kitty.
We did it!
But she might escape.
What if…
Now she's safe and can't escape.
Yay!
-[Ismat] Dads!
-[both gasp]
-We found her!
-You're home!
We were so worried.
Thank you for finding her.
I'm so proud of you, Ismy.
Well, it was actually all my fault.
I shooed Cleo away. I'm sorry.
I'm sure you didn't mean it, sweetie.
And she's safe now.
That's the important part.
[sighs] Now you're all back together,
which I'm sure is how you want it to be.
Just you three.
-Huh?
-What do you mean?
You're so in love with Cleo.
I understand why she's replacing me.
Ismat, no one in the world
could replace you.
Really?
Our love for you
is bigger than the tallest pyramid.
Deeper than the largest tomb.
And it flows stronger than the Nile River.
♪ Nothing could ever alter ♪
♪ The love we have for you ♪
♪ We may be smitten
With our little kitten ♪
♪ But, Ismat, one thing's always true ♪
♪ Love gets bigger ♪
♪ Love gets stronger ♪
♪ There's no need for you to despair ♪
♪ It's never-ending ♪
♪ It keeps extending ♪
♪ Love expands the more that you share ♪
♪ Here is the heart of the thought
We're expressing ♪
♪ Whatever changes we undergo ♪
♪ Our love for you won't ever lessen ♪
-♪ Only grow ♪
-♪ Love gets bigger ♪
♪ Love gets stronger ♪
♪ Multiplies the more that you give ♪
♪ The love we're showing ♪
♪ It keeps on going ♪
♪ Growing just as long as you live ♪
-Oh, Dads, I love you so much.
-[meows]
And you know, Cleo is kind of cute.
Runs in the family, I guess.
[chuckles] I sense Cleo is growing on you.
[chuckles] Yeah. Maybe a little.
Now, grab that caftan.
We have a fashion show to star in.
[dance music plays]
And for our mummazing finale…
Cheer your hearts out for Ismat and Cleo.
[overlapping chatter]
[Mrs. Sanchez] Beautiful!
I didn't know anyone could look that good.
Awesome!
Yes! We own this catwalk.
[purrs]
[theme music plays]