♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive ♪
♪ She is saving our future
By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear
She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
[Ridley] Jones to the Future.
-[Ma] Hee-yaw!
-[laughing]
Get along, horsies.
It was, like, a Cretaceously good idea
to shrink us all down
and hide the Heart of the Museum
in the miniature Old West.
That was all Ridley.
She's brighter than Antares.
Thanks. Once I realized I had
many more powers as a full protector,
I figured I'd use them.
I'm glad the renovations are finally done
and we can put the Heart where it belongs.
Me too. But we better hurry to get back.
Uh… Huh.
My scar's tingling.
That's never a good sign.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Dudette, so do I.
But I think my bad feeling
is 'cause your horse
is standing on my tail.
Ow!
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Sh! I hear something.
Wait here.
Hm.
[cawing]
Ridley, I command you…
Um, tell me everything's okay out there.
What's the mission report, Sunshine?
It's quiet. Too quiet.
-[horse neighs]
-[Mama gasps]
Mama, your scar was right.
We've got trouble.
With a capital T. Who are they?
Bandits. Thieves of the Old West.
Meaner than a snake
and smellier than a mule on Sunday.
Hide your purties and your shinies.
The only shiny that matters
is the Heart.
We can't let bandits steal our Heart.
I have a plan.
Ma, Pa, and Eyes, you head west.
Mama, you and I
will head east with the Heart.
You have to ride
at the Bandits and stall.
-That'll give us time to get away.
-Let's do this.
See you on the other side. Yah!
Those Jones women are heroes.
True that.
Let's get this stampede going.
We got some interfering to do.
-Don't have to tell us twice. Yee-haw!
-Yee-haw!
G-forces are easier
on my behind than all this bouncing.
I hear you, P-dawg, but if those bandits
get a hold of the Heart,
we lose our ability to come to life.
-So bounce away.
-Whoa!
-[neighs]
-[gasps]
Oh no, there's more Bandits,
and they're headed this way.
Hm. Mama, you take the Heart.
Ridley, what are you going to do?
I'll draw them away from you.
No, Ridley. That's too dangerous.
Mama, we're protectors.
Danger comes with the job.
Besides, I got this. Yah!
No! My hat!
I've had it on all my missions.
I got it. Ha ha!
-Nice catch.
-I've still got some moves.
Remember, it's not the hat
that makes the adventurer.
It's the heart beating beneath it.
And you have
the strongest heart I know.
Thanks, Mama.
-Now be careful, my love.
-Of course.
Careful is my middle name.
Which, you know it isn't,
because you named me.
But I'll be careful, Mama. I promise.
Now, go. Keep the Heart safe.
It is the most important thing, remember?
-[grunts]
-[neighs]
[suspenseful music plays]
[horses neigh]
Rats! Nothing shiny here.
I reckon somebody better start talking.
-[Peaches chatters]
-Hold me!
Where's your loot, little lady?
I'll never tell.
-[gasps] No. They've got Ridley.
-[horse neighs]
I should save the Heart.
But I can't leave her. Hold on, Ridley!
Hiyah!
Oh, they ain't got nothing on them
except too many bananers.
Yeah, same with this one.
Minus the bananers.
[horse neighs]
Well, well, well. What do we have here?
Mama, no!
Ridley, I'm sorry.
Here. This is what you're looking for.
Let her go, and it's yours.
Mama!
Ridley, I can't let
anything happen to you. I won't risk it.
[chuckles] Purty. Real purty.
And it's all hearty-shaped-like too.
It'll go great with my new curtains.
-Let's get while the getting's--
-[Dudley] Hello!
Where'd everyone go?
[gasps]
-It's…
-Dudley?
I can't believe you all left
to get the Heart without me.
Sorry, we heard you sneezing
and thought you had a cold.
Oh, it was just allergies.
This dodo has, uh, sensitive sinuses.
Allergies.
-Hey.
-Ridley!
What are you doing? Come back!
Trust me.
Stop her.
Sorry about this, Dudley. [grunts]
Hey, what was that for?
The dust is just gonna make me… Uh…
-Uh…
-Mama, Eyes Team, take cover.
Brace for impact!
Oh!
[grunts]
I got it! Oh!
[all grunting]
Hold on tight. We've got you.
Phew. [chuckles]
Excuse me.
[all grunt]
That was close.
Good work, Dudley.
You sent those Bandits flying, and…
[gasps] The Heart. It's chipped.
That's okay.
[sighs] It isn't.
Mama, what's wrong?
I think I've lost my protector mojo.
So let's find it.
Baby, it's not that easy.
Sorry to interrupt, ladies,
but the sun's a-settin'.
We gotta mosey back to the portal
before it gets dark.
Nice.
If you think regular Bandits are bad,
just wait until you see night Bandits.
Okay, coming. Right, Mama?
-Right.
-Let's go. [chuckles]
I'll follow you anywhere.
Hey there.
[sighs] We're back.
And got to say, having a Compass Eye
comes with some cool perks.
I love being able to travel
in time and space,
and even get small enough
to see Ma and Pa eye to eye.
-Bye now!
-See you later!
-Did you get it?
-We did.
And we took another snap
for the celebration wall.
Oh, this is beautiful.
Just what I needed.
Thanks, Eyes.
I'll put it right next to this one
of Sarah as a young protector in training.
Wait, that's not Mama's usual hat.
No, that was
her old lucky adventurer's hat.
She wore it so much, it fell apart.
I can't believe it's been 35 years
since we expanded the museum
to include this tree.
And for 35 years,
it's held the Heart of the Museum.
Today, we reopen it.
Today, I also resign
as a protector of the museum.
-What?
-You can't!
As much as I love protecting the place
I've dedicated my, well, whole life to,
it's time.
Time for me to hang up my hat for good.
Mama, why?
You saw me out there.
I don't have the jones for adventure
like you do.
Not anymore, anyway.
Maybe I was never that good. Not like you.
Mama…
What happened out there?
Mama chose to save me over the Heart.
She thinks she can't
be a protector anymore.
Oh, she just needs a reminder.
A reminder? Of what?
Of how good she was. And is. Sarah?
Sarah, wait.
I can't imagine my mom
not being a protector.
I mean, look at us.
We made such a great team.
Shame.
She's the greatest protector I know.
No insult intended
to present company.
[laughs] None taken.
I've always wanted
to be half as good as she is.
She was fearless.
Oh, and the best leader.
If only we could remind her of that.
We can. I know we can.
What was Mama's greatest adventure?
-Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
-I don't know. What are you thinking?
That socks should come in pairs of threes,
so when you lose one you still have two?
Whoa. Mind blown.
I know your mom's greatest adventure.
It was ours too.
There it is.
-Mummazing.
-That takes me back.
-What am I looking at?
-Scars. From a really scary fire.
This is how we first became a team.
And joined your most righteous mama.
[sighs]
I remember it like it was yesterday.
[Ismat] Everyone gathered here
to watch the tree's inauguration,
celebrating its addition to the museum.
[Fred] We weren't a herd yet,
or even friends, like we are now.
-Ah!
-Dude!
[chuckles]
[Dante] But in the middle of the ceremony,
some gnarly lightning
from the weather exhibit,
like, struck the tree.
[Dudley] And then it caught on fire.
[Ismat] The museum was in total chaos.
[Peaches] Your mama was trying solo.
[Fred] And we didn't
like each other that much.
[Peaches] In a moment of pure bravery,
instead of trying to escape,
your mama ran into the flame.
-Oh no!
-Goodness.
[Ismat] And she came out all singed
and covered in ash,
holding the Heart of the Museum.
[Fred] The hot metal from the Heart
gave her that scar,
but she didn't care.
[Dante] That inspired us to, like,
come together as a team.
And with Sarah leading us, we got
all the dudes and dudettes
out of harm's way.
[Peaches]
Our team was forged in the flame,
and we saved the museum that day.
Wow. Forged in the flame.
See? Mama is a brave adventurer.
If we can just remind her
of what it felt like in that moment
to be a hero.
♪ Look at all these photos ♪
♪ I'll tell you what I see ♪
♪ A hero who's the model of true bravery ♪
♪ Mama needs reminding ♪
♪ Of who she was back then ♪
♪ And then she'll be a hero again ♪
♪ Each of her adventures ♪
♪ Was bolder than the last ♪
♪ If only we could help her
Recollect the past ♪
♪ If we somehow uncover ♪
♪ A way to way back when ♪
♪ We'll help her be a hero again ♪
♪ Oh, Mama, tell me what it is
I have to do ♪
♪ For you to see
The awe-inspiring hero who ♪
♪ I see in you ♪
♪ We'll help her remember ♪
♪ Who she's always been ♪
♪ We'll help her be a hero ♪
♪ Again ♪
[gasps]
-Eyes Team, huddle up.
-What is it, Ridley?
As a full protector,
I have new powers, remember?
-Including going back in time.
-Why would you want to do that?
I don't know about you,
but I hated seventh grade.
If I use my Compass Eye
on this photo of Mom and the tree,
we could go back to borrow
Mama's lucky adventurer's hat.
As soon as she puts it on,
I know she'll change her mind.
Time travel? [chuckles]
Isn't that kinda sorta extremely risky?
This astronaut only learned a little
about the time-space continuum,
but if there's one thing I do know,
it's that going back can mess up
all sorts of stuff in the present
and the future.
Afraid it's too reckless, Sunshine.
And this is coming from someone
who jumps into black holes.
Yeah. I guess you're right.
Let's go figure out a way
to at least cheer your mama up.
Hm. I bet she'd love a bag of birdseed.
I can do this. I know I can.
I mean, they made me a protector.
I have the power. So why not use it?
I'll be back before anyone knows I'm gone.
Okay, past, here I come! Whoa!
Whoa!
Whoa. It's the museum,
but everything looks kind of old.
Huh. Guess I'm in the past.
Mom, have you seen my lucky hat?
Oh, you lost it again?
[gasps]
That's Mama and Grandma from the past.
[gasps] And there's Mama's lucky hat.
[grunts]
Yes! [gasps]
I did it.
Sorry, hat. I'll return you as soon
as Mama feels like a hero again.
[grunts]
Back in the present.
But where is everyone?
Mama? Grandma?
Anyone know why it's so dark in here?
Hm.
Mama, are you in here?
Did Mama and Grandma
give the tree house a makeover?
Everything looks so different--
-Whoa! Mr. P?
-[woman] Who's there?
-Intruder!
-Don't move!
Uh, got to go. [grunts]
[grunts]
Someone's broken into the museum.
-Who are those guys?
-[tires squeal]
-Hi?
-Come with me if you want to leave.
Uh, who are you?
There's no time. Get in, Sunshine.
-"Sunshine"?
-[man] Hey!
[grunts]
We'd better alert Mr. Peabody.
That should keep those guards
from bothering us, Sunshine.
You called me "Sunshine" again.
Who are you?
Who am I?
Just your friendly neighborhood
space monkey-slash-leader
of the museum resistance.
Well, leader and only member.
Peaches? I'm so glad it's you.
Always nice to see you.
But what on Mars are you doing here?
This is no place for kids.
No place for kids? This is a kids' museum.
Well, sure, but a museum owned
and controlled by Peabody, remember?
[beeps, crackles]
[grunts]
I know you been away for a while,
so let me kindly jostle your memory.
When Peabody took over,
he kicked your family
out of the tree house and moved in.
He forced Mama and Grandma
to work in the gift shop,
fired Lonny, and replaced her
with a heartless security firm.
The worst part?
Peabody locks up the exhibits at night.
Everyone is trapped.
That means no playing together,
no exhibit sleepovers,
no Rotundas concerts, nothing.
No. Why didn't the team stop this?
Team? What team?
Fred, Dante, Dudley, Ismat,
and you, Peaches.
You formed a team
when Mama was little.
No. We didn't. We were never a team.
What? Oh no.
And I hate to hand you a brown banana,
but your mama never really
became the protector we hoped she'd be.
-She never stood up to Peabody.
-[beeps]
I…
I don't believe you.
Mama loves the museum,
and she'd do
whatever it takes to protect it.
Uh… really?
Peaches, will you take me to my mom?
-Mama?
-Ridley?
You're supposed to be at boarding school.
Boarding school? Since when do I go to…
Oh. Right. I go to boarding school.
Um… I just had to come and see…
-Wait, let me see your hand.
-What?
-What happened to the scar you got?
-Scar? What scar?
When the Jones family tree caught on fire.
I don't know what scar,
but I do remember that fire.
The tree was struck by lightning,
and everyone was so scared.
But you went in
and saved the Heart of the Museum, right?
What? Run into a fire? No, thanks.
Plus, I couldn't find my lucky hero's hat.
Too risky.
So without your hat,
you didn't go into the fire?
And never inspired
everyone to join your team.
You shouldn't be here.
Mr. Peabody won't like it.
And he's the boss, so what he says goes.
Oh. Okay. Sure.
Soon as I'm done,
I'll drive you back to school.
I'll just wait outside then.
Hm.
-[twinkling]
-Huh?
[gasps]
Everyone is disappearing from the photo.
Does that mean
when I took Mama's hat from the past,
I somehow messed everything up
and the team never came together?
I have to set things right.
But first, I got to get out of here.
Can you help me escape?
You bet your stars I can.
Thanks.
It was good to see you, Ridley.
We sure miss you around here.
I'll be back. I promise.
Copy that. Now, let's peel out.
There it is.
That vehicle
that's always dropping banana peels.
Just try and catch me. Whoo-hoo!
Thanks, Peaches.
I promise, once I'm done with the past,
you won't be protecting the museum alone.
-[woman] Hold on over there!
-[gasps] Oh come on, portal. Open.
[grunting]
Come on! Ah!
[grunts]
Okay, everything changed
when I took Mama's lucky hat.
So all I need to do is return you,
and everything should go back to normal.
Right?
No way. You found my lucky hero's hat.
Oh. Yup.
I, uh… I saw it in the museum,
so I came to give it back.
Thanks. I could've used this earlier.
You won't believe it.
-This tree caught on fire.
-What?
[gasps] That's not good.
I didn't have my hat, and I totally froze.
Lucky my mom showed up… eventually.
No, no, no, I'm too late.
The fire already happened. What do I do?
Hm…
You look kind of familiar. Do I know you?
I'm, uh…
also a Jones woman.
A distant cousin of yours. Just visiting.
My name's Ridley.
Ridley, huh? That's a cool name.
Have to remember that.
Anyway, nice to meet you finally.
I'm Sarah.
And no big deal,
but I'm a protector in training.
Well, you know
what every future protector needs?
A great team to lead. We should form one.
Nah. I work better alone.
A team would just slow me down.
No way. Having a team is the best.
At least give it a try.
I know just the right museum folks
for the job.
-Whoa!
-[gasps]
-Phew!
-Whoo! Thanks for the catch.
No problem. Sometimes it helps
to have someone by your side.
Huh. Maybe you're right.
I'll see how I like it.
Who did you have in mind?
Dudley the Dodo? Are you sure?
Isn't he afraid of everything?
Not everything.
Just spiders, the outdoors,
and clowns, and starfish,
his own shadow, and teddy bears.
Okay, he's afraid of a lot of things.
-But he's the most loyal friend I know--
-Friend?
I mean,
that's what I've heard about him anyway.
Hello? Dudley?
Ah! Who's there?
Oh, hi, Sarah. And you are…?
A long-lost Jones cousin?
We're forming a team to go on adventures
with, and Ridley here suggested you.
Ah!
Not adventures!
Oh! Oh!
Everything outside of my exhibit
is dangerous and extinction-inducing.
I don't want to go the way of the dodo!
Plus, a team led by Sarah Jones?
She's not "leadership material."
This is coming from someone
wearing a colander on his head.
And what's the colander for?
For protection.
Every day could be doomsday, you know.
♪ You could fall into a volcano ♪
♪ Asteroids hurtle up in outer space ♪
♪ And I don't think it's very bueno ♪
♪ To know that one
Could hit you in the face ♪
♪ One step from extinction ♪
♪ One minute from doom ♪
♪ Out there it could all go boom ♪
♪ There are tornados
And there's lightning ♪
♪ Quicksand exists
I hear it's quite widespread ♪
♪ Mummies and clowns
Are really frightening ♪
♪ I think I'd rather stay here instead ♪
♪ With kitchenware on my head ♪
♪ One step from extinction
One foot in the tomb ♪
♪ Out there it could all go boom ♪
♪ Out there it could all go ♪
Ah!
♪ All go boom ♪
Hm.
Every leader and hero
has to start somewhere.
A journey doesn't start at the end.
Anyway, I think if you gave her a chance,
she might surprise you.
And I know the outside world
can seem scary,
but with friends to look out for us,
we're protected,
which allows us to be brave
and face our fears.
Oh, really? I could have friends?
Uh-huh. Friends who will love you
just the way you are.
So, what do you say?
-Let's dodo-do it.
-[chuckles]
[panting]
This is a lost cause, Ridley.
Everyone knows Winifred stampedes alone.
[chuckles] I see why.
I don't know how much longer
my dodo legs can take this.
Winifred? Don't you mean Fred? Fred!
-What did you just say?
-Fred?
[snorts] How'd you know
I wanted to be called Fred?
You just look like a Fred to me.
Oh good. My parents named me Winifred,
but it never felt right.
I think Fred is much more
of a big, tough bison name.
Well, big, tough Fred,
we're here to ask you to join our team.
No, sorry. I stampede by myself.
No one in my herd understands me.
Why would you be any different?
Well, you got us there.
We might as well
head back to the rotunda.
[panting]
Thank the dodo heavens. [whimpers]
Wait! Fred!
Look, sometimes our true herd
isn't the one we're born into.
It's the one we choose.
Hm.
Well, if you're a part of the herd.
-Uh, what'd you say your name was again?
-Ridley.
Oh. You look like a Ridley.
Anyway, if you're a part of it,
then I guess I'm in. [snorts]
-Now let's move out, folks.
-Whoo-hoo!
Please don't make me run anymore!
So, who's next to join our, um, team?
[chuckles]
[clattering]
Like, ow!
Dante, are you okay?
Uh, ouch. [chuckles]
Yup. I'm fine.
Just another wipeout.
Luckily, Ralph and I are pretty tough.
You got to be more careful.
Careful, huh?
No one's ever said that to me before.
Seems like a totes wise idea.
I know you probably like skating alone,
but we wanted to ask you to join our team.
See, when we open up our hearts
and let others in--
Sure. I'll join. Sounds fun.
Oh. Okay. Great.
-Well, that was easy.
-[piano plays]
Where's that inspirational music
coming from?
Whoops.
-[chuckles] That's me.
-Righteous! [laughs]
What? Ah! Ah!
This is so scary!
Oh! Oh! Ooh!
But also kind of fun.
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
[laughing]
-Come on!
-[laughing]
Wait, shouldn't we be heading
to the space wing?
You said you wanted to see
Peaches the Astronaut.
She doesn't spend much time there anymore.
You can usually find her
here.
Ma, Pa, one more banana milkshake, please.
-Sure thing.
-Put something in the tip jar.
We ain't running this here saloon
out of charity.
No. [sighs]
She looks so sad.
Word around the museum is
Peaches has a secret fear
that became too much for her.
She stopped going up into space.
[gasps] Secret fear.
Wait here.
Hey, Peaches, is it?
Who wants to know?
A friend. One you haven't met yet.
I'm Ridley. Ridley Jones.
What can I do for you, Ridley Jones?
This might just be a hunch,
but are you afraid of heights?
Sh!
The walls have ears.
Listen, I used to be able
to overcome my fears
and go on space missions
with my friend Sylvia Jones.
Oh, she was the bravest.
And it made me brave too.
But in the years since,
my fear has gotten the better of me.
Everything seems scarier now.
Even Sarah over there
froze during the fire today.
We all have fears,
but we don't have to face them solo.
Like you said, Grandma-- I mean, Sylvia
made you brave.
Sarah can too.
I think if you joined our crew,
we could help you
get your stuff back.
-[chuckles]
-Order up.
Keep it. I've got permission for takeoff!
What? After all the work we just did?
Oh, sorry.
We're the size of a spoon, you know.
I can't believe this is actually working.
Which is good, because I have to get this
team together and save the museum quick.
Okay, team. Just one member to go.
-Who is it?
-Ismat.
-What?
-Queen Ismat?
Um, yeah.
Queen Ismat the Irritable?
The Terrible?
-The cranky-first-thing-in-the-morning?
-And last thing at night?
And also all the other times? That Ismat?
-Mm-hm. Let's go.
-[Fred] Are you kidding?
Now that I've got my lucky hat back,
I'm totally not scared of anything.
But if I were scared of something,
it'd be the mummy queen.
-Mm-hm.
-What? Come on.
Ismat might have her queenly moments,
but she's not someone to be afraid of.
-[screams] Uh-oh.
-Intruders! Intruders! Intruders!
You were saying?
Um, hi.
I told you, we're not intruders.
We're friends of the queen.
Ha! A likely story.
[laughs] The queen has no friends.
Silence.
We now present our queen,
Queen Ismat Chione
Jomana Edrice Khepri the Great…est.
-Bowing. Bowing. Bowing.
-Not looking at her in the eyes.
Thanks, Dads.
Now, who dares trespass
on this royal mummy's
sacred and tastefully-decorated domain?
Please, Your Highness?
We're museum inhabitants
who've traveled to your exhibit
to visit you.
Visit me? Without gifts or an offering?
[laughs]
Don't make me laugh.
-[snorts] You can have the dodo.
-Hey!
Are you kidding me? [laughs]
That would never go with my decor.
[laughing]
[clears throat]
Come on, Sarah. You got to do something.
Everyone needs your help.
[grunts]
The intruder! She escaped!
-[gasps]
-[grunts]
-Oh!
[grunts]
Yes!
Don't move,
unless you want your queen pokified.
-[gasps]
-Um, sorry about this.
[screams]
Come on.
[gasps]
What are you just standing around for?
After them. They kidnapped
our sweetums. I mean, the queen.
[all roar]
[gasps] Unhand me, you fool.
Without the queen to rule, the kingdom
could fall into complete chaos.
And more importantly,
my outfit is getting so wrinkled.
-[roaring]
-[Ridley] Go the other way.
There they are! Stop them!
I promise,
dodo shish kebab is not appetizing.
Any more bright ideas?
-Um…
-Sarah, just tell Ismat why we're here.
I'm sorry we did this.
We just wanted to talk to you.
I know what it's like
to have big responsibilities.
And a family legacy to uphold.
It can be scary. And overwhelming.
If you let your guard down,
and your guards down,
and found some friends,
you might find another side of you.
One that isn't so… queenly.
Now that's the mama I know.
Ahem.
Now that was a close one.
-I thought we were all totes extinct.
-Well, some of us are totes extinct.
True that.
Sarah, you were amazing.
I guess I… I was, huh?
Come on, I wasn't gonna do anything
that bad to you all.
Just throw you in the dungeon.
Oh, is that it, Princess?
It's "Queen." [chuckles]
That's the first time
you've said that to each other.
[both] Huh?
Uh, never mind.
Anyway, I'm just glad
you decided to join us, Ismat.
Now you're all a team,
with Sarah leading the way.
And the present should go back to normal.
What?
Everyone's still disappearing.
But why?
Fred, I told you, hands off the bling.
I just touched it.
I am not good with conflict.
I am… Ooh!
Oops! Sorry, dodo dude.
What was your name again? Devon?
This is why I usually fly solo.
Whoo! [chuckles]
Whoa!
I might have brought you all together,
but that doesn't mean I made you a team.
♪ Look at what I've done here ♪
♪ What a mess I've made ♪
♪ I cannot repair
This badly broken dream ♪
♪ My efforts come to nothing ♪
♪ In spite of what's at stake ♪
♪ I tried so hard to make you be a team ♪
♪ You can't force a friendship ♪
♪ Yours was forged in fire ♪
♪ You came together
When the odds were most extreme ♪
♪ Nothing I can change now ♪
♪ I fear I'm doomed to lose ♪
♪ I cannot make you choose ♪
♪ To be a team ♪
[Dudley] Ah!
-Really?
-Are you kidding?
[sighs] I guess my only choice
is to head back
and figure out another way to fix things.
-[crackles]
-[gasps] My Compass Eye. It's broken.
Oh no, no, no. This can't be happening.
Come on. Work. Please.
Yes!
That's not good.
No way. Is that a Compass Eye?
Dude!
You didn't say
you were a museum protector too.
It must be a pretty tough job, huh?
I mean, a tough job for you.
I'm gonna be great at it.
Must have slipped my mind.
Oh. It looks totally busted.
Yeah. It got broken somehow.
And I need to fix it
before I go back home,
to a house which exists in this same time,
and not in the future or anything.
That's some purty fancy metalwork.
You're gonna need a top-notch
blacksmith to fix it, Sunshine.
Sure, but where am I gonna find
a blacksmith at a time like this?
-[humming]
-Oh. Right. Hey, Ida.
Hm. So it's completely broken.
Well, when I hit it enough, it does this.
Zounds!
It is as I feared.
This Compass Eye must be reforged.
Reforged?
Well, if anyone can do it, Ida, it's you.
Hm. Yes,
I might be capable of such a feat.
Melting down the metal
so it can be reshaped.
I must warn you the heat
of my exhibit shall not be enough.
I must forge your Compass Eye
in that dinosaur's volcano.
Oh, the volcano that's right over there?
For a second, I thought you were gonna
say somewhere far away and dangerous.
No, no, no, no, not this replica
made of rubber and plastic.
The real one. Here.
-[all] Whoa!
-[Ismat] O-M-Egypt!
That's a lot of smoke.
And lava.
And magma.
Yeah. This might technically
be part of my exhibit,
but I avoid the real volcano
as much as possible,
on account of, you know,
how totally gnarly and aggro it is.
Ida, are you sure we can't just slap
a Band-Aid on the Compass Eye
and call it a day?
Alas, I fear not.
An item as rare and magical such as this
must be forged in the flame.
Forged in the flame.
[gasps] This is it.
Like the tree catching fire,
this mission could put the Compass Eye,
Mama, and the team together.
Don't worry, Sarah.
If we work as a team, we can do this.
Uh-huh.
Now that we've divvied up
all my blacksmith tools,
we must make haste
for the top of the volcano.
There, I shall set up my station
near the hottest lava and embers.
Wow. Up close,
this place looks even scarier.
It looks like an adventure.
One I can handle all by myself.
Wait, no.
This volcano is super dangerous.
And plus, Ida has so much gear,
we need the whole team
to carry it up.
And speaking of the team,
don't you want to give us a pep talk?
Don't fall in the lava. It's hot.
-Great pep talk. Super inspirational.
-[groans]
This might seem
like an impossible mission,
but I believe in you.
If we do this together
and look out for each other,
we'll reach the summit.
-Let's do this.
-Bisonic!
How are y'all doing back there?
Hanging in there.
I don't think these rocks
are dodo friendly!
Whoa! Ah!
Dudley!
[screaming]
Oh. Peaches, you…
You saved me. Thank you.
That was mighty scary.
But I also feel like
I'm getting my right stuff back.
Let's make a deal, Dudley.
If you ever fall,
I'll be there to catch you.
Always.
-You will?
-Of course.
What are friends for?
Phew!
[rumbling]
-[all] Whoa!
-[Dudley] What's happening?
-The volcano, it's about to erupt.
-Then we'd better hurry to the top.
We need to wait
and take cover until it's done.
You can stay if you want,
but I'm going ahead.
-We have to go together.
-Look, I told you I didn't want a team.
I said I work better alone
and a team would just slow me down.
And I was right.
I can't keep you all safe.
So deal with it, okay?
Sarah, I--
[all] Whoa!
[screaming]
No, we're all gonna fall into the lava.
I know you're broken,
but please, please open just this once.
Are we all deep-fried dodo?
Because I smell barbecue!
No, Ridley used her Compass Eye
and saved us.
Well, you know what they say.
"A broken Compass Eye
is right once a day."
Ah!
Uh-oh. This thing is completely destroyed.
We gotta fix it before…
something bad happens.
[all] Whoa!
[Sarah] Uh, what's going on?
That opening I created
with my broken Compass Eye
must be raging out of control.
And it brought the outside world in.
[elephant trumpets]
[all scream]
The museum. The inhabitants. The exhibits.
It'll all be destroyed.
Not to mention,
we'll all be lavas who lunch.
Only if we don't do something.
We have to fix my Compass Eye
and close the portal
before the next eruption.
-Ida, do you still have all your tools?
-Indeed.
Great. We'll stay here and reforge it
while you and the team
get everyone in the rotunda to safety.
But I… I can't.
Everyone is scared and confused.
They need you to lead them.
Ridley, I lied.
It's not that I haven't wanted a team.
I'm scared to have one.
What if I screw up
or make a mistake or get someone hurt?
Someone I love getting hurt
or losing them.
That's my biggest fear.
I'd rather never be a protector
than be one that fails.
Sarah, I know someone
who's a lot like you.
She's always worrying
and making sure everyone's safe.
Especially me.
And lately, she thinks she's failed
as an adventurer and a protector.
But it's okay to fail.
♪ A hero may not always win ♪
♪ But that's okay ♪
♪ At times you take it on the chin ♪
♪ And that's okay ♪
♪ You can't escape from failing ♪
♪ But heroes keep prevailing ♪
♪ They just learn to say ♪
♪ That it's okay ♪
♪ A hero's not immune to fear ♪
♪ But that's okay ♪
♪ You'll have to learn to persevere ♪
♪ And that's okay ♪
♪ When people need protection ♪
♪ You can't let imperfection
Make you run away ♪
♪ That's not okay ♪
♪ It's not how bad you fail ♪
♪ It's not how hard you fall ♪
♪ It's how you get back up
That matters most of all ♪
♪ You can't win every battle ♪
♪ Can't always save the day ♪
♪ Just try your best ♪
♪ You'll be okay ♪
It's okay.
You're a Jones woman, Sarah.
And Jones women never give up.
Jones women never give up, huh?
Okay, team, enough standing around.
Let's mobilize.
Ridley and Ida will stay
to fix the Compass Eye,
and we've got
scared inhabitants out there.
It's our job to save them, okay?
-[all] Okay!
-Then come on.
-Oh yeah!
-Whoo-hoo! Whoo-hoo!
Are you ready?
Forsooth I am.
I just need a bit of--
Aha! Some hot lava.
We may begin the smelting process.
And as we blacksmiths like to say,
"He who smelt it, dealt it."
[both laugh]
Hurry, okay? We don't have much time.
[adventurous music plays]
Whoo!
[panting]
[laughs]
-We did it, team.
-Hooray!
We did. We dodo-did.
Houston, we have some safe museum folk.
And everything is gonna be all right.
[all scream]
Everyone, get to the stairs.
Oh no! The Heart of the Museum.
Sarah, why aren't you running?
Keep going. I'll be right back.
No. Mama!
Ida, please hurry.
Almost.
Whoa!
[panting]
Got it!
Oh no.
Mama!
[grunts]
-Sarah, grab on.
-Whoa!
[gasps] My lucky hat!
Your lucky hat. It's gone.
It's not such a big deal.
You know, I'm starting to think
that it's not the hat
that makes the adventurer. It's…
The heart beating beneath it.
Oh. I like that second part.
I do too.
Oh no! We're trapped!
-Hiyah!
-[thunder rumbles]
Lady Ridley! Catch! [grunts]
[grunts]
It… It worked.
-We did it!
-Righteous! [laughs]
Galactically great work, y'all! We did it!
Oh, and we did it together.
As a Team. With a capital T.
-Yeah!
-A Team.
[laughing]
I guess we did do it.
-[lemur clears throat] Um…
-Huh?
Now that the lava's gone,
can someone help us down?
Whoops. That was all my doing.
We've got scared, displaced inhabitants
to get back to their homes.
-Ready?
-You all go.
You've got this.
I know you'll keep the museum safe.
-For sure.
-Roger that.
Thanks for believing in me, Ridley.
I promise I'll never give up.
[chuckles]
Thank you, Ridley.
Okay, no bars on the exhibits,
no creepy lighting or security guards.
So far, so good.
Dudley, the banner can't say,
"Featuring Dudley the Amazing."
What? How come?
Because you're not the star
of this celebration, I am.
I mean, the tree is.
Now I just need to convince Mama
not to retire.
But I don't need a lucky hat to do it.
The hat doesn't make the hero.
It's the heart beating beneath it.
And no one's heart
is stronger than Mama's.
I know I can convince her.
Mama? Mama?
I'm in the kitchen.
Mama. Okay. I know you want to retire
and quit being a protector, but I--
Retire?
What are you talking about, sweetie?
But you said…
Ridley, I'm a Jones woman,
and Jones women never give up.
Hurry and eat before we go patrolling.
And keep an eye out for Peabody.
He's been acting really suspicious lately.
I didn't just fix the future.
I made it even better.
-What was that, sweetie?
-Nothing.
Oh! What was that for?
Just… thanks for always being my hero.
And for never giving up.
You're my hero too, Rids.
And I promise I will never give up.
[theme music plays]