♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive ♪
♪ She is saving our future
By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear ♪
♪ She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
[Ridley] Dino Versus Dodo.
See anything out there, Sunshine?
Sandstorm. And it doesn't look friendly.
We'd better go tell Grandma.
There's a sandstorm on the way.
Oh, blast. Let me just get
this one last chunk of fossil.
Cool. One strong bison coming right up.
-[snorts]
-[all grunt]
Now, let's get out of here
before the sandstorm gets us.
-Dante, catch!
-Got it.
Let's get the peck out of here.
Step on it, Ridley.
[all] Whoa!
Must go, like, faster. Ooh!
-[Dudley] Oh!
-[Dante] Whoo!
Grandma, be ready
to close the portal behind us.
We're gonna have to jump.
Everybody, hold on to your hippocampus.
[all] Whoa!
[Peaches] Great butterscotch bananas!
That was a bit close for comfort.
But we made it out with the fossils,
so it was worth it.
Let's get those fossils to your lab
and see what you discovered.
Aha!
Looks like we found the yutyrannus.
Yuty-what now?
I'm a dinosaur,
and even I never heard of that dino bro.
The yutyrannus is a recently discovered
relative of the tyrannosaurus rex.
And what makes
this dinosaur so interesting is--
Oh! It's got feathers. Like a bird.
That's right.
Birds evolved from dinosaurs.
In fact, most paleontologists
consider birds to be living dinosaurs.
Consider my Cretaceous cranium blown.
It's a real bummer
that your ancestors evolved into birds.
We could have been dino bros.
Excuse me.
Birds are far superior to dinosaurs.
We can fly.
Well, most of us can. No offense, Dudley.
Oh. [grunts]
I keep trying.
Wait, birds can, like, fly and stuff,
but they are way teeny-tiny
compared to dinosaurs.
We were some of the biggest,
most megalo-super creatures
ever to stomp and romp the Earth.
Dinos and dodos are both amazing.
That's right, little Dudely dodo.
Birds are still cool,
even if they're tiny.
At least there's some of us left.
-Oh yes.
-Yeah.
-Oh, you tell him.
-Well, low blow.
Huh. Are you saying
dodos are better than dinos?
Maybe I am.
Oh, it is on like pteranodon.
♪ Everybody in the whole rotunda ♪
♪ Let's hear it for the lizards
Who are bringing the thunder ♪
♪ You ever seen a bird
Who inspires wonder? ♪
♪ I've only seen this tiny dodo
Blab and blunder ♪
♪ Dinosaurs, the children adore us ♪
♪ No little kid
Pretends to be a bird-asaurus ♪
♪ You descended from us
Does that make you all maddy? ♪
♪ Come on, little bird
Tell me, who's your daddy? ♪
♪ Drop the beat ♪
♪ Dinosaurs can roar
But birds just tweet ♪
♪ Dante, I applaud your elocution ♪
♪ But thankfully
We've undergone an evolution ♪
♪ Your species was big
They were all colossal ♪
♪ But ask me who's my daddy
Yours is a fossil ♪
♪ I know, dino, you're big as a rhino ♪
♪ But that's the reason
For your meteoric decline-o ♪
♪ You should have evolved
As well as you've rapped ♪
♪ When the climate changed
You didn't adapt ♪
♪ Drop the beat ♪
♪ Dinosaurs are absolutely obsolete ♪
[both] ♪ Drop the beat ♪
Dante, Dudley, you're friends.
You don't need to argue like this.
Yeah, 'cause dinosaurs are obviously best.
Pfft.
You mean birds are.
If you two can't settle things
by dropping rhymes,
maybe you can
settle things by leading herds.
Hit it, Peaches.
♪ If you got a bird beef
And your fossils are a-chillin' ♪
♪ I can cure your illin'
Like a bison penicillin ♪
♪ You gotta lead a herd and you gotta-- ♪
Um, I think Fred is saying that whoever
is best at leading a herd, wins.
Leading a herd shows
you have great strength of character.
Like me.
Are you two sure you want to do this?
Step aside, dodo-bro-bro.
Let the dinosaur show you how it's done.
-Whoops. Sorry.
-[snorts]
Stampede!
Whoa!
-Oh!
-[bison] Stampede!
Well, that doesn't look safe at all.
Whoa! [grunts]
[grunting]
My feathers!
He's covered in fountain grass. Mm!
Delicious fountain grass.
Ooh, yummy, yummy, yummy!
Ah!
Come on, wings. Now would be
an excellent time to be more wingy.
[bison] Ooh!
[Dudley] Hey, ooh! Ah!
[screaming]
[grunts]
[groaning]
Peaches. Thank beakness it's you.
I'll always be there
to pull you up, Sunshine.
Nice job, Dudley.
You outran that herd
for almost half a mile.
I did? That means I led the herd.
[gasps] I win! Birds win.
Bird-ya!
Uh, that was, like, an accident.
It totally doesn't count.
Sounds like herding
didn't solve the issue.
But don't worry,
I have another idea how to settle this.
Queen Ismat decrees that whoever
solves the riddle of the Sphinx…
That's me, Thoebe the Sphinx.
…will be deemed the winner.
Hmm. What's a good riddle for you two?
Got to think. Got to think. Let me see.
Oh! I've got a good one.
[clears throat]
When people see my big round eyes,
they say that I look very wise.
So please say hi. I'm quite a hoot
when dressed up in my feather suit.
The wise winged hooter is the dodo bird.
Obviously.
You chose… poorly!
[all scream]
Dante, you want to try to solve it?
A hoot?
Dude, that sounds like an owl to me.
Yup, that's it. An owl.
You did it, Dante. Yay for you.
Well, Dudely Dudley,
looks like I won the riddle.
Dinos are best. [chuckles]
Maybe you guessed right,
but the answer was an owl,
and owls are birds,
so that still means birds
are the number one bestest.
[snorts]
Oh, we still haven't settled anything.
Maybe not, but I think
this here space monkey
might have an idea how to solve
this conundrum once and for all.
Way I see it, whichever of y'all
is best prepared for space
ought to be the winner.
This is gonna be one
bodaciously giant leap for dino-kind.
Who needs to leap when you can fly,
which is a thing that birds do sometimes.
Count us down, Sunshine?
[all] Three, two, one.
Blastoff!
[Dudley] Wait. What's going on?
What's going on? Stop!
Bogus!
[both screaming]
[beeping]
Uh, Peaches, what's going on?
Not sure.
The simulators were on autopilot.
There shouldn't be any way to mess it up.
Leave it to those two
to mess up the un-mess-uppable.
[screaming]
I command you to make it stop.
Sweet banana sundae!
They're going into virtual hyperspace!
-Birds.
-Dinosaurs.
-Birds!
-Dinosaurs!
[screaming]
[both grunt]
Dante, Dudley, are you okay?
This has gone far enough.
You've always been friends.
You shouldn't let anyone
divide you up into different groups.
I'm with Ridley.
Y'all should call it a draw.
Yeah, I think you should
shake hands and be friends again.
-Okay, sure.
-Fine with me.
Now, let's clean up this mess.
You know, I would've totally won
if those simulators didn't go all loopy.
We should pick our own challenge.
Word. And since I know
I can win at anything, I'll let you pick.
Oh, well, I, um… I pick, uh…
Sand surfing!
Sand surfing?
You better bring your avian game, Dudely.
Oh, I will bring it and wing it. Hm.
Oh no. I got to go tell Ridley. Oh.
Okay, Dudley, dude.
First one to surf back through the portal
and into the museum is the winner.
Yeah. Okay.
And when I win, that will prove
that birds are better than dinos.
Never gonna happen, dodo bro-bro.
I say, less rhyming and more slime-ing.
I mean, surfing.
Whoa! Ha!
[grunts] More surfing is what I meant. Hm.
On your mark, get set…
Dodo!
Wait a second!
I don't know how to sand surf!
And even if I did,
I'm not near brave enough to do this.
Whoa!
Whoa! Ah! Eek! Ah! Oh! Ay!
Dudely? Dudely! Oh!
Whoa!
Ah! Ah.
[panting] I sure wish Dante was here.
He'd know what to do.
Brontobunga!
Dante! You came to save me!
Well, yeah.
Dino or dodo,
you're still my little birdy buddy.
Whoa! This river's getting rough.
-Bogus!
-Ah!
Dante, grab on!
[both grunt]
Whoa! Uh-oh.
My claws are slipping!
Dante, I got you, buddy!
Whoa. Thanks, Dudely.
I was about to be dino-donezo.
Yeah, that was a close one.
Hey, look, we're hanging
onto another dinosaur fossil.
I wonder if this dino had feathers.
You know, it would actually be
kind of cool to have feathers.
And it would have been amazing
to live in the time of dinosaurs.
I can't believe we let anybody
divide us up and make us argue.
Yeah, who cares
if dinos or dodos are best?
No matter what, you'll always
be my little dodo Dudely dude.
You'll always be my big dino bro.
-[both scream]
-[Dante] Oh no!
[Grandma] There they are, Ridley.
Grab on!
[all grunting]
Thanks for coming to save us.
Righteous rescue.
I just hope you've ended
your argument by now.
We sure have. I don't want
to fight with my little dodo bro-bro.
It doesn't matter who's better.
What matters is our friendship.
That sounds perfect.
Now what do you say we head on home?
Yes, please. I need to rest my wings.
But on our way home, want to race?
Oh, you know it, Dudely.
[all laughing]
[theme music plays]