♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive ♪
♪ She is saving our future
By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear ♪
♪ She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
[Ridley] Peaches' Space Race.
Another stamp, Ridley.
You had to be extra brave
to find Pedro's lost toy in that volcano.
Mr. Fish is safe and sound.
Well, that's not the only exciting news.
Your grandma here called in some favors,
and a new exhibit
is coming to our museum today.
-No way!
-Yes way.
And let's just say it's out of this world.
[gasps] Is it the Zenith exhibit?
The very one.
It's got artifacts
from the real space mission.
Even the Zenith shuttle itself.
Wow! Ooh, I gotta go tell Peaches.
Peaches, we've got a surprise for you.
What a kettle of mules.
I got a surprise for y'all too.
Oh, oh, a stack of banana sandwiches?
Better.
Better than sandwiches?
Whoa, is that a comet?
Ooh, let me see.
Stellar, ain't it?
That there's the Jemison Comet.
It only orbits Earth every few years,
but when you catch it,
ah, it's a sight for sore eyes.
-So you've seen it before?
-Sure have.
I was just a tiny little chimp then,
and seeing that comet
streaking across the cosmos,
it made me want to be an astronaut.
Folks think space exploration
is all about the destination,
but getting to the moon don't mean a thing
if you can't appreciate
the beauty all around you.
Oh, speaking of space exploration…
Oh, yeah. Peaches, guess what.
The Zenith exhibit is here,
with the real shuttle and everything.
Zenith. Mm.
That means she's gonna be here.
Who?
Cookie.
[Cookie] Alrighty,
keep the planetary samples together
and let's get our girl Zenith notched up
to a 60-degree angle. [chuckles]
That's where she shines.
She commands such respect.
Don't she know it.
Do you know her?
All too well.
Cookie was my rival in astronaut training.
No matter how hard I worked,
she'd beat all the records.
And when it was time
to recruit a chimp for the Zenith mission,
guess who got to go.
Was it you?
It was not you. Got it. Right.
That must have been hard,
but you are not in training anymore.
Maybe you two could be friends.
Ha! That's as likely
as a snake stubbing their toe.
Cookie really knows
how to shrimp my grits.
Peaches? Is that you, girl?
Look at this.
The dream team back together.
Oh, I've been hoping
I'd get to see your museum,
but it's been wild
touring all over the world.
Let me tell you something, Junior.
Royals? They love space.
I told you not to call me Junior.
It's nice to meet you, Cookie. I'm Ridley.
Peaches has told us,
uh, so much about you.
Oh, well, if I know Peaches,
I bet it's still shrimpin' her grits
that I beat all her records.
Oh yeah? Well, I'd like
to see you try and beat me now.
Is that a challenge?
'Cause you know
how much I like a challenge.
You bet your banana it is.
How about we race to Jemison's Comet.
First chimp to pitch their flag
on the highest point wins.
Like, wins what?
[both] Glory.
A space race sounds fun,
but, um,
I don't exactly have a crew on hand.
Uh-uh.
You're not backing out that easy.
You can borrow some of mine.
A space race? I am so in.
Then you're hired, cadet.
All right then.
Ridley and Dante, you're with Cookie.
Fred, Ismat and Dudley'll ride with me.
-Dino-mite.
-Count me in.
-Amazing!
-I can't wait to see space again.
And I can't wait to see
the look on Cookie's face when I beat her.
-Three…
-Two…
[both] …one, blastoff!
We're ahead.
Eat my space particles, Cookie.
Can we do a quick loop around Earth?
I want to see the pyramids from space.
We don't have time for sightseeing.
We've got a Cookie to crumble.
I can't believe
I'm in the real Zenith shuttle.
Believe it. You haven't even
seen what this baby can do.
-[Ridley] Whoo-hoo!
-[Cookie] Whoa!
[laughing]
Got any snacks in here, Captain Cookie?
Wouldn't be a space tour without 'em.
Here, catch.
I'll just slow this ship down
a little so you can float away.
Oh, Ridley. You gotta see this.
Whoa.
Mind blown.
Hey, check it out. There's Taurus.
That's a bull, you know.
Practically family.
Oh. Any dodo constellations?
Quit wiggling, Dudley.
In fact, no one move.
It affects our speed.
Huh. Sorry.
[Peaches] I think I see a shortcut
round the dark side of the moon.
[all groan]
Any chance we can get a better view
of the moon, or literally anything?
Almost there.
Boom! First to the comet.
Now let's go plant our flag.
-Oh, I'm gonna need a minute.
-Whoa.
I got the dodo dizzies.
No time. Cookie is right behind us.
Did you see that nebula?
I didn't even know that color existed.
No. We saw space, as in the empty part.
[sighs] What a ride.
Just like our days back in training, huh?
Oh, I get it.
"Back in training,"
where you always beat me.
Well, not today, Cookie.
Can't have you
falling behind and wasting time.
And I thought queens were bossy.
Wow. I can't believe
we're this close to the comet.
It's like a whole other world.
Even I've never walked on a comet before.
It's not what I expected at all.
Let's gather samples.
If you're trying to distract me,
it ain't gonna work.
I'm headed for the finish line.
Oh, catch up with you later then, Junior.
You will not. And don't call me Junior!
Ridley, you want to assist me?
Like a real astronaut? Yes, please.
[groans] As queen,
I demand to be with the fun team.
I hate to say it,
but I agree with the princess.
Y'all, this is a race, not a field trip.
-Come on, Dudley.
-[gasps]
[Peaches] We're winning this.
Ah, this is more like it.
Peaches was really
taking the fun out of space.
Being up here
is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
I hope she's having some fun.
No, all she cares about
is planting her flag.
[gasps] Peaches can't plant her flag.
It'd be a disaster.
Captain Cookie dude,
there's nothing wrong with losing.
No, a disaster for her.
Look what's below all this dust.
The comet is held together by ice.
But this close to the sun,
it's melting, and fast.
So if Peaches plants a flag…
The ground will crack
under her and Dudley.
We've gotta warn them.
That Cookie thinks
she's the monkey's bananas.
-But today is Peaches' day.
-[panting]
Hooray!
[both panting]
This is one small step for chimp kind
and one giant leap
for me proving that I'm the best.
I'm nobody's Junior. I win!
[both scream]
[grunts] This doesn't feel like winning.
Help! Dodo down! Dodo down!
-[Ridley] Oh no.
-Dudes!
Dudley.
[Dudley grunts] Save us!
Well, Junior, looks like you won.
Aw! Pickles in a jam jar.
I thought finally beating you
would feel great, but it just feels…
-Sticky?
-We'll get you out of there.
Dudely. Grab on to Ralph.
[grunting]
[grunts] Thank beakness.
Come on, just let me help you.
[grunting]
All right.
[grunts]
What? You just assumed
old Junior here would need saving?
Nah, astronauts never assume.
They research.
Wait, you were actually doing tests?
I thought you were trying
to distract me so you could get ahead.
You kidding?
How could I worry about the finish line?
I just landed
on a comet for the first time.
Ha! The whole point of being
a space explorer is exploring space.
♪ We chart a course for exploring ♪
♪ Then get distracted somehow ♪
♪ Sometimes we end up ignoring ♪
♪ The beauty of the here and now ♪
♪ The countdown begins ♪
♪ The course has been set ♪
♪ But don't let the end be your guide ♪
♪ You're on a remarkable journey ♪
♪ Enjoy the ride ♪
♪ Even the best navigation ♪
♪ Often can lead you astray ♪
♪ Life's not a mere destination ♪
♪ Don't miss the stars along the way ♪
[both] ♪ The planets fly by ♪
♪ We hurtle through space ♪
♪ Our universe endlessly wide ♪
♪ We're on a remarkable journey ♪
♪ Enjoy the ride ♪
Thanks for reminding me
what really matters, Cookie.
I got so carried away with winning.
I didn't even stop to think that…
I'm dancing on Jemison's Comet!
I wonder what tiny little Peaches
would think of this.
I think she'd want to enjoy it.
How about we take the long way down.
We've got some sightseeing to do.
[cheering and laughing]
Wow.
So, uh, congrats on your win, Ju--
I mean, champ.
First to the top of the Jemison.
Finally, a record you can't beat.
[laughs] I'm glad you're always
nipping at my heels.
You drive me to be a better astronaut.
Aw.
You know what?
Watching you
inspires me to be better too.
Race you back to the museum?
[chuckles] Oh, you are on.
Last one there's a rotten banana.
[theme music plays]