♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive ♪
♪ She is saving our future ♪
♪ By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear
She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
[Ridley] Ridley's Christmas Carol.
-Happy holidays. Time to go ho-ho-home.
-[both laugh]
Have fun. And Merry Christmas.
Don't "Merry Christmas" me.
I hate Christmas.
Oh, the cheerfulness and mirth…
[gasps] …and money that I can't make
because we're closed for business.
Are you kidding, Mr. P?
Christmas is the best.
It's my favorite holiday.
Bah humbug.
Somebody's got a case of the Scrooges.
I'll be back in the morning.
-Is it time yet?
-Hold on. Didn't hear Peabody leave.
-[clattering]
-[Peabody] Ow! Who put that wall here?
-[door closes]
-Ah. Now Mr. P is gone.
I can't wait.
For what?
Uh, my very first Christmas
with the Eyes Team.
Oh, right, you've never
spent Christmas here before.
-But, Ridley, I gotta warn you--
-Merry Christmas, everyone.
The Eyes might not have
the spirit you're looking for.
[barking]
[laughs]
It's Christmas Eve, everyone.
-Yikes.
-No way.
-I hate Christmas.
-What a foul celebration.
Wait, what?
[Ma] Timber!
Ridley! Look out!
Oh no! The Christmas tree!
Or as I like to call it,
Christmas kindling.
Chopping up this tree
will keep us warm for the whole winter.
Um, you live in a place
with indoor heating.
And why would you chop up
a Christmas tree?
We don't celebrate Christmas
in these parts.
What? Why?
Christmas is the best time of the year.
I don't understand what's happening.
I was so excited to finally
get to spend Christmas with you guys.
-But, like, why, dudette?
-It's awful.
Thing is, Mr. P hates Christmas,
so he wants everyone else to hate it too.
[growling]
[sighs] It's true, Sunshine.
He closes the museum,
makes us take down the decorations,
and has all his employees--
-That's me. I'm all of them.
-Do inventory on Christmas Day.
So we can't strut our stuff.
Or stampede or even move all day.
Ugh. We hate Christmas.
-That's awful. How did I never notice?
-I covered for your mom and grandma.
They made such a great Christmas
in the tree house.
You never came down to see this.
So you guys
have never had a real Christmas.
No trying to sleep
while you're waiting for Santa to come?
Or squeezing the stockings
to guess what's inside?
Or singing Christmas carols?
No, but we do know a Christmas carol.
Yup, we learned it from Mr. Peabody.
♪ Christmastime is terrible ♪
♪ Christmas costs me money ♪
♪ Christmas is unbearable ♪
♪ Humbug ♪
What? That is not a Christmas carol.
This is a Christmas carol.
♪ Candy canes, falling snow ♪
♪ Presents wrapped with a bow ♪
♪ Wreaths and tinsel, mistletoe ♪
♪ That's the joy of Christmas ♪
-♪ Children smile, bells will ring ♪
-[jingling]
♪ Carolers laugh and sing ♪
♪ There's a glow on everything ♪
-♪ That's the joy of Christmas ♪
-[whale song]
♪ Christmas spirit is beyond compare ♪
♪ Hope and kindness fill the winter air ♪
♪ You'll see it everywhere ♪
♪ Ornaments on the tree ♪
♪ Lights as far as you can see ♪
♪ With your friends and family ♪
♪ That's the joy ♪
♪ Of Christmas ♪
♪ That's the joy of Christmas ♪
Well, I think we know what happens next.
I get to show you
the true meaning of Christmas,
kind of like in my favorite
Christmas story, A Christmas Carol.
Come on. I'm gonna read it to you.
"…and Scrooge loved Christmas
from that day forth."
The end.
Whoa. I laughed, I cried.
I totally felt the Christmas spirit.
-Is it over?
-Yup.
[sighs] You should warn a bird
when a story has ghosts.
But the Christmas ghosts showed Scrooge
how to stop being mean
and start being sweet.
Scrooge reminds me of someone.
Hm, I just can't put my hoof on who.
[Peabody]
What is all the joyful merriment in there?
Wait, got it.
Scrooge reminds me of Peabody.
Merry Museum Mayday, everyone.
-Let's go!
-Let's get out of here!
The decorations are still up.
What is the meaning of this, Ms. Jones?
Mr. Peabody,
everyone deserves a proper Christmas.
Even the exhibits--
I mean, everyone in the museum
who is alive, like Lonny.
I am talking about Lonny.
No, they don't,
and Lonny certainly doesn't.
I wish there was a way
to give you some Christmas spirit.
[chuckles] Impossible.
Now, take all of this down.
-Oh, and give me that.
-No.
-Yes.
Ms. Jones! Ah!
[gasps]
[all scream]
Is everyone okay?
[grunts]
Two eyes, two legs,
two decorative wings.
[sighs]
Still room for improvement, but I'm okay.
I know a stylistic change of scenery
when I see one.
What happened?
-I have a feeling this is Christmas Past.
-I have a feeling we'd better, like, hide.
Hiding left. Hiding right.
Oh no, they're gonna run into me!
[gasps] Whoa!
Huh.
They can't see or hear us.
Ho-ho-no-no.
I hate Christmas. Boo, Christmas lights.
Bah humbug. [grunts]
I bet this is Mr. Peabody's past,
and we have until midnight
to make him love Christmas,
just like in A Christmas Carol.
[Dudley] Mr. Peabody, I presume?
-What's up, Mr. Peabody?
-Hi.
Ah! Get back!
Mr. P, meet Peaches,
Dudley, Dante, Fred, and Ismat.
Why are the exhibits moving?
And talking?
[snorts] Hi, Scrooge. Oh, I mean, Peabody.
[panting]
What is happening?
Um, something I'm hoping
you don't remember tomorrow morning.
Do you recognize this?
Of course I do. It's the museum.
But wait. Wait.
This isn't the museum today.
-It's…
-Your Christmas Past.
Eh, too big. Hm?
Too small.
Huh.
Just right.
That's me.
Welcome to the past, Mr. P, dude.
As you can see here,
you, um, totally like mustaches.
-Very on-brand. [chuckles]
-I used to love that mustache exhibit.
[chuckles] Little did I know that one day,
my face would sport an even better one.
Hello? Hello? Young man?
He can't see you.
The tree. Wait. I know this day.
I… I hate this day.
Ms. Jones, why are we here?
There must be
something important for us to see.
No! Absolutely not.
Nothing important to see here at all.
Ooh, I do love
putting the star on the tree.
It's beautiful.
It is, isn't it?
Yes. Everything in here is.
I love this museum
almost as much as I love Christmas.
Well, aren't you delightful?
-What's your name?
-Filbert.
Filbert, huh? Well, that's adorable.
You're welcome here anytime, Filbert.
You seem like you're one of us.
One of you? Uh, thank you!
Today is my favorite day.
I dare you to take that star.
No way. I double dare you to do it.
Fine. Chicken.
-[boy] Huh.
-[gasps]
Hey, you can't do that.
Leave that star alone.
Then come up here and stop me.
I, uh… I…
[clears throat] What's going on here?
[gasps] Mom! The star is missing!
It can't be. I just put it up there.
He did it.
Yeah. That kid's the thief.
Nuh-uh. That other kid stole it. [scoffs]
That star's been
with the museum for decades.
-How could you do such a thing?
-Now, Filbert, what happened to the star?
I…
I didn't take it. I… I swear.
He's lying.
I saw him throw it in the trash.
We all saw it.
I'm sorry, Filbert,
but you'll have to leave the museum.
But I didn't.
You heard her. Leave now.
No.
[sniffles]
You loved the museum,
and you didn't steal the star.
No. I didn't. I would never.
No wonder you hate the museum,
and Christmas.
[weeps] I hate the museum
because it is an old building
filled with old things
that no one cares about.
It has nothing to do
with that beautiful, beautiful star.
Can we leave now? I hate the past.
I… I demand to leave this nightmare.
There's something in this past
we're supposed to see.
But what?
[sighs] I don't know.
[gasps] The star.
It started Peabody's hatred of Christmas.
Maybe if we can get it back?
Whoo-hoo! [laughs]
Watch out, dudes!
Ugh. Total tail fail.
-[clock chimes]
-Oh no!
I bet we're about to leave Christmas Past.
Without the star.
[all scream]
[all grunt]
This must be Christmas Present.
Another Christmas, another inventory.
Uh, I hate to be the bison of bad news,
but he doesn't seem
any more in the Christmas spirit.
Wait, a Christmas tree.
Maybe he did change.
I'm gonna go with not quite there yet
at giving Peabody the Christmas spirit.
[chuckles]
Ho-ho-ho. One last thing
to count on inventory night.
Hot biscuits and gravy.
His heart is at least two sizes too small.
Yeah. Well, let's see what's happening
in the rest of the museum.
Twenty-seven dung beetle dung balls,
28 dung beetle dung balls,
29 dung beetle dung balls.
That's a lot of dung beetle dung balls.
Wait, why is she smiling?
She should be frowning.
Sad. Miserable.
She's doing inventory
instead of home with her family.
-Christmas really is for family.
-See?
And that's why it warms
my Christmas heart
to be spending it with you.
Even if it means
counting the bug collection.
One slug. Ugh.
Two slugs. Ugh. Three slugs. Ugh!
Well, I'll be my uncle's niece.
We're helping Lonny with inventory.
Thanks again
for helping me with inventory.
It's gonna go way faster
with all of you here.
Anytime, Lonny.
And sorry Peabody
makes you do this on Christmas Day.
Ah, it's okay.
If I'm honest, I kind of like it.
Christmas is about being with family.
You guys are my family.
Okay, now I'm getting
the Christmas spirit.
Get over here, you big galoot.
I'll admit, Christmas isn't so bad,
but I'm not feeling Christmassy enough
to forgive Peabody.
-No way.
-Me neither, Sunshine.
This is what I have to say about that guy.
-Why, I never.
-I know Peabody's terrible.
But I kind of feel bad for the guy.
Imagine being that miserable. Oh,
sometimes I just want to give him a hug.
Maybe we can, uh, listen a moment longer?
I think we're getting to him.
-[clock chimes]
-No. We need a little bit longer.
-We're out of time.
-Whoa!
Christmas Future.
-The great unknown.
-I sure hope our story has a happy ending.
[gasps] Look at the person
who looks like you, but not like you,
'cause they're older than you.
Oh. That is you. I mean, Ridley.
That's me?
Looks like you're coming home
from college.
Mama, Grandma, I… I'm home.
Why are the doors locked?
Mama? Eyes?
Where is everyone? What's going on?
Ah! This is straight
out of my worst nightmare.
Well, well, well.
Looks like my evil plan worked after all.
What evil plan?
Oh, just the worst Christmas ever.
Mama?
[gasps] An eviction notice?
Peabody kicked us out of the museum?
Mama? I'm here.
Oh, Ridley, I'm so glad you're home.
Why is everything in boxes?
Where is everyone?
We have some bad news.
You tell her. I can't.
Peabody is closing the museum.
We all have to find a new place to live.
Oh, I'm so sorry, dear.
What? He can't do that.
Apparently he can.
He sold all the artifacts.
It looks like it was his plan all along.
[chuckles]
Mama, Grandma, I'm so sorry.
I should've been here.
No, you're having the greatest
adventure of them all: college.
And you're here now.
Besides, we can't let Peabody
ruin our last Christmas here.
Yes, we can.
He kind of did already, right?
How can you think about
Christmassy stuff when our home is gone?
A house doesn't make a home.
Not even a cool tree house.
A house is a home
when people you love are in it.
You're here, and Grandma's here.
That's what matters.
[barking]
And don't forget about us.
[overlapping speech]
I missed you all so much.
Aw, you decorated.
Ever since you taught us
to love Christmas,
we never miss a chance
to pull out the Christmas lights.
And compete over who has the best
Christmas lights display at their exhibit.
-Ho-ho!
-Galactically festive.
-Mummazing.
-[Dante] Bodacious.
[Fred] Love it.
Merry Christmas, everyone.
Merry Christmas.
-[barking]
-[laughing]
Mama, you're right.
Wherever we go,
as long as we're together, it'll be home.
[all laughing]
[muttering]
Christmas isn't
about the place or the presents.
It's not even about the decorations.
Christmas is about being
with the people that you love.
Aw.
[all laugh]
How can there still be mirth?
I made the worst Christmas possible,
and they're still happy.
How can that be?4
[gurgles]
[sighs]
♪ I thought
I humbugged their holiday joy ♪
♪ I should have ruined
Their Christmas cheer ♪
♪ With all of the schemes
That I've worked to deploy ♪
♪ This mirth I see here
Should just disappear ♪
♪ No way should their elation persevere ♪
♪ So why are they all singing
Hand in hand? ♪
♪ Am I feeling something new? ♪
♪ Could it somehow be
That I like Christmas too? ♪
[gurgles]
♪ Don't be foolish ♪
♪ Christmas is awful ♪
♪ All holidays are ♪
♪ I learned that lesson so long ago ♪
♪ Back when the Joneses
Said I stole that star ♪
♪ This foolish tableau
Is all just a show ♪
♪ So you'll know where to shove
Your merry ho-ho-ho ♪
♪ But something shines inside me ♪
♪ Like that star
High atop the Christmas tree ♪
♪ Could it be
The Christmas spirit lives in me? ♪
♪ No, I shall not be coerced ♪
♪ I had it right at first ♪
♪ It's clear that Christmas is the worst ♪
Bah humbug!
[clock chimes]
Oh no, we need more time.
[all scream]
[sighs] That sleep was gnarly.
I had a dream that Mr. P was once a kid.
Oh, me too. With a fake mustache.
So it really happened.
Do you, uh, remember
what we saw in the future?
Sorry to say, but I do.
The future was really scary,
but it's not set in stone.
If we can show Peabody
the good of Christmas,
maybe it won't all turn out the same way.
Eh. He seemed pretty convinced
after the star shenanigans
he'd never be a fan of Christmas.
Too bad the little star
flew into an exhibit.
Wait a minute. That's it.
The star was thrown
into the Arctic exhibit.
I bet it's still there.
We need to go find it.
[overlapping speech]
[Peabody snoring]
[mumbles]
All right, team,
let's be on the lookout for the star.
Huh. The star could be anywhere.
And this holiday sweater is cute and cozy,
but, uh, I still have no pants, so…
[groans]
It's getting… getting cold. Eh!
I'm trying to stay
as sweet as a ripe peach,
but the truth is,
we might not find it, Sunshine.
And speaking of sunshine,
the sun is gonna set soon.
Whoa! Killer wave of wind.
Ah!
Dante!
I got you, Dante.
Huh. Thanks, Ridudely.
Snow makes for the, like, softest landing,
except for when it's, you know, spiky.
Ow!
The snow is spiky?
Totally. Ralph landed
on something mondo-pointy.
Wait a minute, that's…
-[Dante gasps]
-[all] The star!
[grunts] Got it!
What is that?
A stampede?
That's no stampede. That's…
[all] An avalanche!
[Dudley whimpers]
This dodo doesn't want to go-go
covered in snow-snow. Ah!
[Peaches] I got you, Sunshine.
You always do that at the right time.
I got an interstellar sixth sense.
-Your horns!
-[Fred] Oh, your crown!
[barking]
Uh, right now, I am too Cretaceously cool.
Whoa! Everybody, come quick.
We're gonna need another ride.
[grunts]
-[grunts]
-[screaming]
-Gotcha!
-Go, Dante.
Let's Christmas kick it.
We just have to get the star
back to the museum in time
to change Mr. Peabody's Christmas spirit.
When we get back,
I'm not leaving my nest for a whole month.
This dodo needs a staycation!
Ho-ho-ho!
[laughs]
There. Right where it belongs.
-Oh my stars.
-Thank beakness.
[snoring]
[mutters]
What's going on, Ms. Jones?
I… I had the strangest dream,
and you were there.
I know it was you.
You're blaming me for your dream?
You know what I mean.
And that strange dodo was there.
And he was…
he was talking about his fears.
And he had a lot of them.
Explain yourself.
Like you said, Mr. Peabody,
it was just a strange dream.
Ms. Jones, I told you,
Christmas is canceled.
[gasps]
My… my star.
-[Mama] What's going on?
-Everything okay?
[gasps] Hey, what a pretty star.
I love the way she razzle-dazzles.
-That's been missing for ages.
-I'll never forget the day it disappeared.
I kicked a boy out of the museum,
only to discover he didn't steal it.
I felt really bad about that.
Me too.
I always wanted
to say I'm sorry to that boy.
I looked for him,
but I never saw him again.
I don't think he ever came back.
It is… [gasps]
…as beautiful as I remember it.
Fine. Fine, fine, fine, you can have
your Christmas shenanigans,
but only until tomorrow.
And Lonny?
Yes, sir?
You don't have to work on Christmas.
Inventory is canceled.
Yippee! Thanks, sir!
Get off of me! Ugh!
Bah hug-bug.
It worked. We can celebrate after all.
Merry Christmas, everyone.
[all] Merry Christmas!
[laughs]
♪ There's a star on the tree ♪
♪ And we're right where we should be ♪
♪ Here with friends and family ♪
♪ That's the joy ♪
-♪ That's the joy of Christmas ♪
-♪ There's a star on the tree ♪
♪ And we're right where we should be ♪
♪ Here with friends and family ♪
♪ That's the joy of Christmas ♪
[laughing]
A very merry ho-ho-dodo to you.
Get your slice of banana Yule log.
Mm, delish.
A yuletide yeehaw!
Merry Christmas, sweetie.
I'm so proud of you for finding that star.
Merry Christmas, Mama.
It ended up being the best one yet.
But, Mama, I saw something.
It's about Peabody's plan.
I need to tell you about it…
after we sing Christmas carols.
-[all laugh]
-[Fred] Merry Christmas!
[theme song plays]