In a place full of mystery
Where the past comes alive
There's a hero of history
Who is ready to thrive
She is saving our future
By protecting our past
She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last
Ridley Jones
Daring and bold and courageous
Guards the museum with pride
Ridley Jones
Her sense of adventure's contagious
With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side
Ridley Jones
Wearing her trademark fedora
No challenge can get in her way
She won't ever give in to her fear
She shines when adventure is near
Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day
Ridley Jones
Ready, Pet, Go.
Well, would you look at that?
-Out of this world.
-Mummazing.
Ooh, it looks like
a fossilized triceratops skeleton.
Sure does.
I've found dinosaur bones before,
but never anything this well-preserved.
There's one bone missing.
Has anyone found anything
that looks like a tibia bone?
Are tibia bones round and squishy?
No? Then not me.
I found this diamond,
but it royally clashes with my crown.
I've got something. Is this it?
Indeed, it is.
Well done, Ridley.
O-M-Egypt.
I guess it wants to see me.
Bananas! Aw, little guy
just wants to play fetch.
Good boy.
Well, aren't you just
the cutest little fossil I've ever seen?
Is it really that cute?
How cute!
I wonder what
we should call our little dino bro.
What should we name you? How about Tibby?
Short for "tibia."
Sounds like Tibby agrees.
It's time to get this fossil
back to the museum.
Welcome to your new home, Tibby.
Now let's find someone
who can take care of you.
Not it. I'm not a dog guy.
-Who doesn't like dogs?
-Me!
So drooly.
What about you, Dante?
Tibby could be
the perfect dino pet for you.
Oh, I'd love to have Tibula around,
but I'm only 65 million years old.
I'm not ready for that commitment.
Taking care of a pet
is a Jurassic responsibility.
How about you, Fred?
Living with Tibby could be bisonic.
On second thought…
Sorry, sunshine.
My exhibit isn't exactly pet-proof.
Hey! Lay off the licking, Tibbs.
These boots are made for space walking.
I would adopt Tibby,
but I already have a cat.
And Cleo's so much work… for my subjects.
Queens don't do litter boxes.
We're sorry, Ridley.
We all royally adore Tibby.
-We just, like, can't adopt him.
-It's okay.
I just want to find someone
who loves him as much as I do.
Wait. That's it.
I love Tibby. I should adopt him.
So, what do you think? Can I keep Tibby?
Please?
Your grandma and I
sort of have our hands full.
Literally. Now that
these scrolls are restored,
we've got to return them
to the Library of Thoth.
You and Grandma won't have to do a thing.
I'll take care of Tibby all by myself.
Protector's honour.
A pet is a big responsibility.
You have to be sure you're ready.
I'm always ready.
I mean, I've done a great job
so far, haven't I?
But it's only been one afternoon.
A pet is a lifetime commitment.
I can handle it, no problem.
I'm an advanced protector now, remember?
I suppose you're right.
A journey doesn't start at the end.
And he sure is cute.
Thanks, Mum. I won't let you down.
I'm still not a dog fan,
but I do love a good adoption ceremony.
With great joy and queenly pleasure,
I now pronounce
Tibby Jones officially adopted.
Yeah!
Now you're all mine, Tibby.
Are you ready to join us
for museum rounds?
Oh! Tibby!
Let's see. We've bathed the sloths,
oiled the robotics exhibit.
We just have to dust the pottery. Whoa!
Tibby! Stop!
Come back!
Okay, minor setback. No big deal.
We cleaned up the mud,
and now we just have to dust the pottery.
Whoa!
Tibby, no!
Back on track. I can handle this.
Not now, Tibby.
We have to finish cleaning up
before we can play.
Don't worry, Ridudely.
I got this. Go long, Tibula.
Wait, what is that?
Whoa. Where did Tibula get this?
That looks like one of the scrolls
Mum and Grandma restored today.
I recognize that stamp.
It's the symbol of Thoth,
the God of Wisdom.
Thoth? That's right.
Grandma was bringing them
back to the Library of Thoth.
My dads told me that library
is protected by so many booby traps
only the most advanced protector
can even get in there.
Legend has it Thoth didn't want
any of his knowledge stolen,
so he put a curse on the place
in case anything went missing.
If that scroll isn't returned by midnight,
the Library of Thoth will self-destruct.
Not the library!
Oh, no. All those other scrolls,
all of that ancient knowledge,
will be lost.
And it will all be my fault.
Technically, it will all be Tibby's fault.
Not helping, got it. Sorry.
I can't believe I let this happen.
My job is to protect history,
and instead,
I might be the reason it gets destroyed.
Plus, that scroll means Tibby wandered off
into a dangerous, cursed, ancient library,
and I had no idea.
-He could have got hurt.
-That's okay, sunshine.
Tibby looks happier
than a mule in a mud mask.
This time. But that's not the point.
Maybe Mum was right.
Maybe I'm not ready for a pet.
I love you, Tibby,
but I'm in way over my head.
I'm sorry. I have to un-adopt you.
For your own good.
I'll find you a new home
as soon as we get back, okay?
But first,
there's a library that needs saving.
-You got it.
-Sure thing.
You weren't kidding
about those booby traps, Princess.
How did Tibby get out?
Come on, Eyes Team.
We've got a scroll to return.
Why is dodo always on the menu?
Looks like we've got company.
Tibby, how'd you follow us?
Tibby, no. It's not safe.
Nice doggy.
Nice job, Dudley.
-I told you, I am not a dog guy.
-Let's keep going.
Of course. Tibby's been here before.
He knows where to go.
Royal!
Nice work.
-Jurassick!
-O-M-Ra!
Bisonic!
Now all we have to do
is put the scroll back.
That wasn't so bad, right? Whoa!
Not so bad?
Okay, let's think.
If we can just deactivate the booby trap…
Tibby, no!
-Go, Tibula!
-Yeah!
Let's do this.
Over here!
All right!
Yippee!
We did it.
-Fantastic.
-Now let's get out of here.
Tibby!
What's the matter, sunshine?
The mission was a whopping success.
I know, but I already
made up my mind to give up Tibby.
I can't take
as good care of him as I'd like.
But you already adopted him.
He's part of your herd.
Totes.
There's no take-backsies on adoption.
Yeah, you can't abandon him.
As the last of my kind, I know a thing
or two about how it feels to be all alone.
Plus, Tibby's starting to grow on me.
He just needs a little training, is all.
I wasn't born
a stellar astronaut, you know.
I had to train before soaring into space.
Just like you had to train
to be a protector.
Really? You think so?
Pets take work, there's no doubt
But you made a promise
That you'd stick it out
That's what love's all about
Training's tough, I suppose
But look at that cute horn
On his cute dino nose
Plus, it's the choice you chose
It may not be easy
But, Ridley, don't you see?
We don't give up when it's our family
Buckle down, don't quit yet
It pays off
With all the snuggles that you get
Oh, how you'll love your pet
Soon enough, he'll be trained
You'll forget the things
He's eaten, chewed or stained
With all the love you've gained
I know it won't be easy
But this I guarantee
I won't give up
'Cause you're my family
And we're here to help.
Thanks, guys. Wait a minute.
Where did Tibby go? Tibby?
-Oh.
-Passport, please.
For saving the Library of Thoth?
For learning that love is forever.
Yeah. It is.