♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive ♪
♪ She is saving our future
By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear
She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
[Ridley] Dante's Jurassic Rescue.
Here we go. Runway is clear for takeoff.
Which means we're clear
for the next round of banana bowling.
Come on, Dudley.
Give that coconut the old dodo heave-ho.
I fly like an eagle, I bowl like a dodo.
Hi-yah!
[all scream]
Huh? One banana?
My best banana bowl of all time!
[laughs]
Good job, Sunshine,
but I reckon we're gonna need
a stellar final bowl if we're gonna win.
Oh, I'm not worried.
Our best bowler is up next.
Do your stuff, Dante.
-Huh?
-Dante?
Dante, we need your bowling wizardry
to help our team
win the coveted Golden Banana.
Created by your favorite Egyptian queen,
which is me, your favorite.
[sighs]
Uh, right. Banana bowling.
I got you, Dudley, dude.
-Dante!
-Cool your jets!
[grunts]
Might wanna launch your coconut at
that constellation of bananas over yonder.
Oh yeah. Right.
Oh no. This is coconuts.
Mondo apologetics, Mrs. Sanchez.
No apologies necessary. Game on.
-[groans]
-Dante, is something wrong?
You never banana-bowl so badly.
Like, sorry.
I just can't get into my bowl space
when I keep thinking about those eggs.
Eggs? What eggs?
Come on, dudes. I'll show you.
Look at those dino eggs.
They look so lonely with no mommy
or daddy dino dudes looking out for them.
I hope you're okay out there,
little eggy dino dudely-dudes.
Sorry, team,
but I just can't focus on bowling
when I keep worrying about those eggs.
Don't be sorry, Dante.
Caring about others is one of the things
that makes you a truly righteous dino.
Oh, thanks, Rids.
There's no reason you need
to keep worrying.
Now that I've got my Compass Eye,
we can go wherever or whenever we want.
Let's just go check
to see if they're okay.
[adventurous music plays]
[gasps]
-Wow!
-[Ridley] Amazing!
[pterodactyl screeches]
I know I say this all the time,
but this really is Jurassick.
♪ Come follow me, let's take a tour ♪
♪ Where dinos roam and stomp
And dinos soar ♪
♪ It's totally Jurassic ♪
♪ The climate here is warm and wet ♪
♪ Ask any dino dude or dino-dette ♪
♪ It's totally Jurassic ♪
♪ Way cooler than the Ice Age ♪
♪ It's utterly bodacious ♪
♪ Oh, give me that precise age ♪
♪ That's after the Cretaceous ♪
♪ When life on Earth was in its prime ♪
♪ The land they call
The land before your time ♪
-♪ It's totally Jurassic ♪
-♪ Totally Jurassic ♪
♪ Big teeth and tails were all the rage ♪
♪ So you can keep
Your lame old modern age ♪
-♪ I'll stick to classic ♪
-♪ Totally Jurassic ♪
♪ An age of endless summer ♪
♪ It's pre-pre-prehistoric ♪
♪ And not to be a bummer ♪
♪ But the ending's meteoric ♪
-♪ Totally Jurassic ♪
[chuckles]
Oh, look, a nest full of eggs. How cute.
Oh! A nest full of eggs!
Hold on, little eggy dudes.
Dante's coming.
That's an affirmative on the eggs,
but no dino parents in sight.
[dinosaur] Help! Somebody, like, help me!
Looks like this just became
a rescue mission. Come on.
BRB, little dino dudely-dudes.
-Help!
-Don't worry.
We're the Eyes Team
and we're ready to help.
Mega-thanks. I was, like,
guarding my nest of eggs
and only stepped away
for a micro-moment
to munch on some tasty ferns.
But then a wicked rock
totally fell on my spiky tail.
Not cool.
Lucky for you, tough bisons
are built for moving big rocks.
[grunting]
Oh! [grunts]
Uh, I think rocks were heavier
in dinosaur times.
I got a plan.
We could totally build a, uh…
-Wait for it.
-We're waiting.
Oh, right.
We could totally build
a Triassic teeter-totter.
I know you love those eggs,
but now's not the time
to build them a playground.
I think I see what Dante means.
If we put one side of a teeter-totter
under the big rock, we can move it.
Yeah, what Ridley said. Huh.
Megalosuper plan.
But primo-please put a rush on it.
I need to get back to my eggs.
[grunting]
Did anyone order a fallen log?
And this should rock it up a notch.
One bisonic-saurus leap on the way!
Whee!
Righteous cannonball, Fredster.
Yeah, I know. [snorts]
[laughs] My tail is as free
as a feathered creature
that my kind will evolve into
millions of years from now.
[chuckles]
Oh, what happened to that rock
after it flew up into the air?
Huh? Fred rocked it up too many notches.
Watch for falling boulders!
Big smashy falling rocks.
Run!
[all screaming]
My eggs!
Lonely little eggy dudes!
Rids, P-Monkey, hop on.
Blast off, Dante!
Oh, feathers.
Go!
The eggs are in the basket.
Repeat: eggs are in the basket.
-[cheering]
-Yeah!
Total thanks.
I'd tail-bump you but, you know, spikes.
-Ralph appreciates the non-spikage.
-[all laugh]
Are all the eggs okay?
[chuckles]
Let's see. Here's Crunchy and Gurgles.
[chuckles] I named them already.
Here's Roly-Poly, Herbie, Needles, and…
[gasps] Stegman?
Where's Stegman?
Oh no! One of my eggs is missing!
Look! Over there!
That dino took Stegman.
[sobs]
My poor little eggy Stegman!
I'm, like, totally too slow
to catch an oviraptor like her.
Don't worry.
The Eyes Team will bring that egg back.
Without a crack.
A crack would be wack.
No more rhymes. Now's not the time.
-[groans] Now I'm doing it.
-[chuckles]
-Let's go.
-It's tail time.
[screeches]
We got you cornered
like a june bug in a jelly jar.
Give us back that egg
before Fred has to act tough.
Yeah.
Wait, what do you mean, act?
-[screech]
-[all gasp]
[hissing]
[mumbles]
Get them before they get away.
Come back here, you egg-swiping varmint.
[screeches]
-[screeches]
-[grunts]
This would be a lovely time
for me to learn how to fly.
[grunting]
[whimpers]
[grunts]
-Whoa!
-[hisses]
Whoa, girl. Whoa.
Whoo-hoo!
Ride 'em, Ridley!
Whoa! [grunts]
That dino bucks like a bronco.
How are your vitals, Ridley?
I'm fine, but they're getting away.
Those raptors messed
with the wrong dino dudely-dude.
[hissing]
Ah!
Come back!
Whoo!
[grunts]
I bet this looks so cool.
Oh yeah. [laughs]
[gasps] Oh no. Whoa!
Oh! Bogus.
Double bogus.
[roar]
-Oh no!
-Dante's trapped.
Oh, shooting stars.
[hissing]
Just like so many problems in life,
the solution is bowling.
I'm gonna need to, like, bowl a strike.
[gasps] Do it for little Stegman,
the dino dudely-dude inside this egg.
He egged a strike.
-All right!
-Gotcha.
[screeches]
Dante, you were amazing.
-The dino dudely-dude abides.
-[chuckles]
Come on.
Oh, my little Stegman is safe again.
Megalosuper thanks.
I'm just happy knowing
that these eggs
are back in the nest where
they'll be totally loved and cared for.
And not a mule tail too soon.
Them critters are making to hatch.
-[squeaking]
-[all] Aw!
They're cuter than dimples on a donkey.
[gurgles]
Could I… Could I hold Stegman?
Of course you can.
Hey there, little dino dudely-dude.
Little stegosaurs,
say hello to your Jurassick Uncle Dante.
-[all] Uncle Dante! Uncle Dante!
-Whoa!
Sun's going down. We should
probably get back to the museum.
Probably.
But I think we can let Uncle Dante
enjoy this a little longer.
Hey, watch your little spikes. Ow!
[laughs]
I reckon we'll need a stellar
final bowl if we're gonna win it.
Don't sweat it.
Now that I know those dudely-dudes
are loved and cared for,
I'm in my perfect bowl space.
[laughs] We did it!
We won the coveted Golden Banana!
[chanting] Dante! Dante! Dante!
Dino-dudely banana bowler,
I, Queen Ismat, am honored to present you
with the coveted Golden Banana.
Dante? Where'd he go now?
What could be more important
than the coveted Golden Banana?
Thanks, little dino dudely-dudes.
You gave me the inner peace
to banana bowl the perfect strike.
You make your Uncle Dante proud.
[theme music plays]