♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive ♪
♪ She is saving our future
By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear ♪
♪ She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones ♪
[Ridley] Mummy Makeover.
I'm feeling a bit underdressed, y'all.
I knew I should've
brought my black-tie space suit.
It's okay, Peaches.
You're still cleared and ready for takeoff
in the museum's newest exhibit.
Portraits of royalty throughout history.
Thanks, mummy friend.
Isn't this exhibit the best?
A collection of kings and queens
all in one place.
Though something,
or should I say someone, is missing.
Me.
[all] Jura-sick!
Thanks, everyone.
It's only fitting
that I grace this exhibit
with my queenly presence.
[sighs] I just hope I fit in.
They're all so fashionably fabulous.
Relax, Ismat.
You're just as royal as they are.
Come on, everyone.
Let's check out the rest of the exhibit.
You go ahead.
I have some portrait hanging to do.
[chuckles] Young lady,
this exhibit is for royals only.
Right, Queen Victoria?
Indubitably, King George. [laughs]
Oh. Of course. I mean, why wouldn't it be?
I just thought maybe I could hang
a picture here, since I'm a queen too.
[both laugh]
Oh. You're serious.
Well, you certainly
don't belong in these hallowed halls.
Look at your common clothes,
your, uh, wraps.
Hey, my wraps are sarcophagus chic.
Ugh! And your green skin.
Royals can't have green skin?
My dear, never in all my painted days
have I seen a green queen.
-You simply can't hang with us.
-[laughs]
-Surely not.
-The very thought of it.
Oh. I guess I really don't
look like them at all.
Fan sadder, please.
[both groan]
Ismat, is something wrong?
I was going to hang my picture,
but the other portraits
don't think I'm royal enough.
-No way.
-Way.
I thought I was, but I guess
my clothes and wraps and green skin
don't scream "Queen material."
[sighs] Maybe they're right.
Maybe it's time I gave myself
a mummy makeover
for a new portrait that's more royal.
[gasps] I'm thinking accessories.
Any ideas?
-Pearls, dude.
-Scepters.
Rubies.
Don't count your mules
before they're washed.
That stuff's scattered
all over the museum.
And borrowing them is gonna be
harder than catching a comet by the tail.
I don't care how hard it is.
We can do anything
as long as we work together.
-Right, Ridley?
-Yeah.
But do you really need
a bunch of extra royal stuff?
You might look
a little different from the others, Ismat,
but you're still a queen.
Oh, okay.
I guess I didn't need
to join the royals anyway.
Stop the sad fanning.
[sighs] If it's important to you,
then it's important to us.
-Count me in.
-Really?
Oh, thanks, Ridley.
Okay, Sunshine.
First up on Ismat's list: pearls.
And there's bound
to be a humdinger in one of the clams.
Wow. Look at the size of that.
Oh! My dodo heart.
[Peaches] Oops, I forgot to mention.
Watch out for Mark the hangry shark.
Dudes, I've got three words for you:
clam fishing.
Okay, maybe two words, but still…
Great idea, Dante.
We'll use my rope
to lower someone into the tank,
but they'll need to be small and light
so we can reel them up
before they become a shark snack.
Who, me? But I don't have my water wings.
[chuckles]
Dudley, you've got this.
You're the bravest dodo I know.
I'm the only dodo you know.
And I'm the only dodo you'll ever know.
Last of my kind, remember?
Yes, but also, one of a kind.
And we believe in you.
[grunts]
My team needs me. Let's dodo do this.
[adventurous music plays]
[screams]
-[growls]
-[Ismat screams]
[horses neigh]
Yee-haw!
Mummazing new pearls: check.
Fancy flawless cape: check.
Seriously, Ismat,
you're still a queen no matter what.
You don't need all this stuff.
Um, yeah, I do.
If I want to hang with the portraits,
I need to be as royal as royal can be.
[sighs] Peaches, please tell me
we found everything on Ismat's list.
Almost, Sunshine.
Last up is a royal scepter.
Ida's guarding it in the armor exhibit,
but I'm sure she'll let you borrow it.
I shan't let you borrow it.
-You shan't?
-Please.
Apologies, but I am sworn
to protect the royal scepter
unless I am bested in combat.
Then I challenge you to a duel.
Forsooth, let the battle commence.
Now remember, you shall know defeat
should your backside meet the floor.
-Huh?
-You lose if you fall on your butt.
-How that be?
-Yikes!
[both grunting]
Whoa!
Look out!
-Ah ha!
-[grunts]
-Get her, Ridudely.
-O-M-Ra.
-Ha!
-Whoa!
-No!
-Huzzah!
Let me help you up.
And may I say,
for one of your size and age,
you are a formidable foe.
Thanks, Ida. And sorry, Ismat.
I guess we're not getting
that scepter after all.
But we can't give up now.
We're this close
to completing my makeover.
No, a queen fights her own battles.
-Ida, I challenge you to a joust.
-[all gasp]
My makeover, my duel.
You're in for a hoof-load of trouble.
-Tallyho.
-Here we go.
-[Dudley] Yay!
-[Dante] Yeah!
[Ridley] Come on, Ismat.
[gasps]
-They did it! They won!
-[cheering]
Oh, that was simply smashing.
As promised, I bequeath this to you.
Mummerific! [laughs]
-Thanks, Ida.
-My pleasure.
[triumphant music plays]
-Tubular.
-Looking good.
It's a lot.
I know, right?
I'm definitely royal enough now.
Speaking of which…
New look, eyesore.
Lou, could you be a dear
and paint me a brand-new portrait?
Um, minus the green skin.
Wait, what?
Ismat, without your green skin,
your painting won't look like you.
Exactly.
I have to look like the other royals.
And none of those
kings or queens are green.
Now, if you'll excuse me…
[sighs]
If this is important to Ismat,
it's important to me.
I guess. [clears throat]
Presenting Queen Ismat Chione
Jomana Edrice Khepri the Great.
Greetings, fellow royals.
My word. What a pleasant surprise.
Now you look like a proper queen.
You simply must join us.
Really? O-M-Ra!
I mean, very well, then.
[chuckles] Now that is a royal portrait.
Yes, you did a fine job covering up those
dreadful wraps and that greenest of skin.
Agreed?
-Oh, absolutely.
-[team gasps]
Oh, thanks…
I think.
Ismat, aren't you, like,
happy with the new you?
Um, of course.
I got everything I wanted, right?
And they accepted me.
Then why doesn't this feel good?
-[alarm rings]
-[gasps]
Uh-oh. Museum mayday.
That sounds like the fire alarm.
But what could have set it off?
Oh. Fire!
This is not a drill!
Flaming biscuits! Water!
Every royal for themselves!
[royals clamoring]
Water's a painting's worst enemy.
It'll melt them all away.
Not on our watch.
Keep those paintings high and dry.
[Dudley] Oh!
[grunts] Wait for me!
Oh, moving is tough.
-Peaches, can you turn off the sprinklers?
-You betcha.
But I'll need an extra set of hands.
Let's blast off.
Help! I'm too important to melt!
Hold up, I-dog.
If you get super soaked,
your wraps will unravel.
There's no time to wait.
The paintings are in trouble.
[grunts] That's more like it.
Don't worry, Your Royal Highnesses.
Everything's gonna be all right.
-Thank heavens.
-Cheers, love.
A queen has to keep her people safe,
no matter what.
Oh! Fashionably on time.
Ismat, are you okay?
More than okay.
She was positively stupendous.
I've never seen such bravery.
Dudes, that's because
Ismat is royally righteous.
And she never, ever gives up.
That's the mark of a true queen.
You know what? You're right, Ridley.
I was always royal enough.
I don't need any extra stuff.
I'm still a queen, even if I'm green.
[upbeat music plays]
♪ I don't need to change a thing ♪
♪ To truly be a queen ♪
♪ The skin I'm in is perfect ♪
♪ It's my favorite shade of green ♪
♪ So save your pearls for other girls ♪
♪ They're not my kind of glam ♪
♪ All I need is to be the queen I am ♪
♪ I'll be me ♪
♪ I'm already royalty ♪
♪ I'll just be me ♪
♪ I don't need a scepter
To confirm my sovereign style ♪
♪ The queenly streak inside of me
Is stronger than the Nile ♪
♪ So keep your gowns
Your capes and crowns ♪
♪ Though it may sound bizarre ♪
♪ Because you rule
When you're being who you are ♪
♪ I'll be me ♪
♪ By imperial decree ♪
♪ I'll be me ♪
♪ That's the queen I'm meant to be ♪
Queen Ismat, would you do us the honor
of joining our regal ranks?
OMEgypt, of course.
But it looks like
the water ruined my painting.
Which is okay,
because that wasn't the real me.
And we want a real picture
of the brave green queen who saved us all.
[sighs] It's a perfect fit. Mummerific.
Let's give our green queen
a royal round of applause.
-[all cheer]
-Ismat!
[theme song plays]