Fixed & Synced by bozxphd. Enjoy The Show.
[PACHO IN SPANISH] Amado Carrillo Fuentes!
The Lord of the Skies!
How fucking elegant, motherfucker.
- Don't tease.
- God damn, fucker.
- Your little brother?
- Yes. Alvaro.
Come here, son.
- You also get a hug.
- Sir.
How are you doing?
320 million kinds of okay.
Doesn't it smell like
the fucking U.S. Treasury in here?
- This half is yours.
- Yes?
- Don't forget it.
- All right. We came at a good time, then.
A Tuesday like any other, Pacho.
You know how it is.
Motherfucker.
- Let's go to the house.
- Let's go.
- All right. Son, do you like margaritas?
- Of course I do.
Great, because I have a Margarita for you.
She'll suck you dry.
[IN ENGLISH]
Welcome to Mexico, motherfucker.
[IN SPANISH] Let's go.
Take the money and destroy the plane.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
First off, Senator Martin and I
would like to thank you
for having us down, Ambassador.
But, you gotta know what's going on
in Washington.
Folks are wondering
if we're gonna win this thing.
And as senior members
of the Appropriations Committee,
those questions are directed at us.
Now, everyone's proud of the work
you guys did to bring down Escobar.
And it's particularly an honor
to meet you, Agent Peña.
But cocaine continues to flow north,
and the American people wonder
if the Colombians share our enthusiasm
to take this threat head-on.
Our colleague, Senator Helms,
put forward some tough language on them.
But we wanted to come down here
and get the real from you all.
See firsthand what's at stake.
See how and... if we can give you
all the support you need.
Let's extend the senators every courtesy
while they're here.
Their mission is a priority.
They ask... you answer.
Thank you.
[PEÑA] Money makes the world go 'round.
Legal or illegal, good guys and bad guys,
we all chase money.
For the DEA, it's about budget meetings
and kissing the right ass
to keep the funding flowing.
But if you're a trafficker,
getting the money is easy.
It's holding onto it that's hard.
["C.R.E.A.M." PLAYING]
♪ C.R.E.A.M., get the money ♪
♪ Dollar, dollar bill, y'all ♪
♪ I grew up on the crime side... ♪
[PEÑA] In the early days,
cash was flown back to Colombia
on the same planes
that carried coke into the States.
Then it was converted into pesos,
or, if you were Pablo Escobar,
stuck in a hole somewhere.
One trafficker died with so much cash
buried on his property, when it rained,
the river downstream became clogged
with bills that had washed free.
The biggest problem with illegal money
is the trail that it leaves.
Once upon a time, American banks
would take your money, no questions asked.
That changed when President Nixon
signed the Bank Secrecy Act,
requiring all U.S. banks
to report transactions
involving more than $10,000 in cash.
And from that law,
money laundering was born.
The first stage of money laundering
is called placement,
and Cali had it down to an art.
Bringing workers from the comunas
to the U.S.,
where their job was to buy money orders,
each just under ten grand,
so they wouldn't be reported.
No I.D. was required.
And the orders could even remain blank
until they were deposited or cashed.
Once they bought a bunch of money orders,
they packed them up and sent them south
to a land of sunshine and lax oversight.
Switzerland on the Caribbean: Panama.
Since they didn't regulate wire transfers,
Panama was the perfect place
for the second stage of money laundering:
layering.
And here's where the master goes to work.
The behind the scenes MVP
of any drug cartel is the money launderer,
the guy that takes the dirty money
and scrubs it clean. Here's how:
The money orders were deposited
into local bank accounts,
and then bounced through shell companies
and limited partnerships,
creating an untraceable web of phony
purchase orders and transaction reports,
wiping clean the money's criminal origins.
But no matter how well you hide it,
money always leaves a trail.
And the best way to hurt the Cali cartel
was to find it.
♪ Dollar, dollar bill, y'all ♪
[FEISTL] Cali. Muy hermosa, right?
Fuck you, Chris.
The man asked me if I had a partner,
and your desk is across from mine.
You really fucked me, man.
You gonna ride a desk all the way
to Special Operations Unit?
Yeah, as a matter of fact, I am.
Agents Feistl, Van Ness...?
- Feistl.
- Welcome to Cali.
- Gracias.
- Captain Calderón.
[IN SPANISH] We're happy to be here.
And what brings you to Cali?
We've got some addresses
we want to investigate.
Cartel-related?
Not necessarily.
What a surprise.
DEA agents that don't trust us.
How did that work out
for the last two guys?
Friend, in Cali, there are more
corrupt cops than there are churches.
You don't trust me? I understand.
But if you want to get anything done
in Cali, you need the police's help.
If not me, someone else.
Not my rule.
- I understand.
- Good.
The addresses are linked
to cartel financial operations.
We want to put eyes on them.
See if any of the dots start connecting...
You've come a long way to connect dots.
We work with what we've got.
Unless you can tell me where I can find
Gilberto and Miguel Rodríguez.
If they didn't own half of the city,
I couldn't even be sure they exist.
The Rodríguez brothers are ghosts.
[PEÑA IN ENGLISH] It was true.
While the terms of surrender
were being finalized,
the brothers had gone underground
to avoid capture.
They abandoned their swank estates,
secretly moving to new homes,
where they could continue
running their empire
without setting foot
in one of their legitimate businesses.
And all this while Chepe continued
to expand their New York operation.
But sometimes, even the best get unlucky.
A computer glitch in Monaco
led authorities to notice
that one limited partnership
had multiple accounts at the same bank.
When they looked closer,
they found it had ties to hundreds
of bullshit accounts across Europe.
And they all led back to one bank...
right here in Bogotá.
Lucky for us, the president
had given the DEA our best weapon yet:
the Clinton list.
If we suspected a company
of working with traffickers,
their name went on the list.
And then they were banned
from doing business with U.S. companies
and U.S. companies were banned
from doing business with them.
You get fucked both ways.
And you want to know
what the best part is?
We don't even have to prove it.
We just... put you on the list.
And the OFAC takes care of the rest.
How can I help you, Agent Peña?
[PEÑA] Armed with the threat
of the Clinton list,
we could get pretty much
any information we wanted,
and that's how we were able to give
Cali's number one money launderer a name:
Franklin Jurado.
Because it was illegal
for Colombian citizens
to have U.S. currency in their possession,
a money launderer became more
than just a connection
to the financial institutions
that washed their cash.
For all intents and purposes,
he is their money.
Jurado was the perfect bridge between
the narcos and the world of high finance.
He spoke five languages
and traveled on multiple passports.
He married an American girl he met
while at business school in the States,
took her down south,
and got her in on his action.
That American passport was solid gold
in any Caribbean bank.
Jurado was smooth.
But now, we knew his name.
These are cash transfers.
The accounts are controlled
by a man named Franklin Jurado.
- You know him?
- Of him.
[IN SPANISH]
He served as director at Interamericas.
- The Rodríguez brothers' bank.
- Mm-hmm.
They later gave him a more important job.
Do you have an address for Jurado?
I can get it for you.
So what happened
since the last time I saw you?
Are you going to take these men on,
or what?
- I'm going to do my job.
- And your bosses?
Do they know what you're doing?
[IN ENGLISH] No comment.
["DANCE WITH ME" PLAYING]
♪ Dance with me ♪
♪ In my world of fantasy ♪
♪ Won't you dance with me ♪
♪ Ritual fertility ♪
I was thinking...
maybe I could come with you.
Oh, come on, this could be our last chance
to travel like we used to.
- Remember that place in Milan?
- With the leaking roof?
On your birthday.
And that terrible risotto.
That balcony.
The brothers are pushing now, baby.
They are opening more accounts.
- It's dangerous.
- I don't care.
How high are you right now?
Hey, fuck you!
Give me your passport.
I can't stay in this apartment anymore,
Franklin.
I can't watch another movie with subtitles
by myself.
I don't want to listen to the cartel wives
talk about their husbands...
- With an English degree from Harvard...
- Please don't tell me I can teach.
Then what did you want me to say?
Fuck.
We'll do this another time.
[IN SPANISH] The dining room is over here.
You have a room over here.
You have another one over here.
And here, you have the living room.
The dimmer is over here.
And you can adjust the light.
Well... you get the idea.
- No. I don't understand.
- What don't you understand?
Does this seem normal to you?
You indicated to Mr. Rodríguez
you were uncertain about returning
to the North Valley.
And that's why he bought me a palace.
With dimmers.
Please tell Don Miguel thank you,
but I need to think
about his generous offer.
We have that dinner tonight.
With your friends?
With the investors.
They're not going to like
the six-month delay.
And I think it's best if we don't mention
the Rodríguez brothers by name.
I know you're embarrassed by what I do.
I know you did it for your family.
But if these people like everything
they hear tonight,
you'll have your own security firm
the second these six months are up.
- [BOTH] Ready!
- Good!
A choir!
[CHUCKLES]
All right, say bye to Dad.
We're leaving.
- [ALMA] Bye.
- [VERA] Bye.
All right. Let's go, or we'll be late.
Will you make it on time?
If you're wearing the dress
with the flowers, yes.
[PAOLA] Let's go, girls.
[CÓRDOVA]
Today is a busy day for us, boys.
Bosses have meetings all day
at the National Hotel.
I need you to pre-sweep
each and every location on this schedule.
And I don't want a bunch of cars parked
like bullshit, blocking escape routes.
- He's looking at you, Montez.
- Of course I'm talking to you, you idiot.
Don Miguel's team on channel six.
Don Gilberto's, channel eight.
Jorge says that the DEA is visiting Cali.
Two agents from Bogotá. They're new.
They're working with the National Police.
But they don't have warrants.
They're tourists.
They need permission
to wipe their own asses.
Regardless, while they're in Cali,
we'll be watching them.
- That's your job, Enrique, my brother.
- Yes, sir.
That's all, gentlemen.
Communicate. Stay safe. Get to work.
I have to duck out early.
It's a work thing for Paola.
Of course.
Do you want to practice your English?
Starkman, the American lawyer,
arrives today.
Can you pick him up from the airport?
Aren't you worried about the tourists?
The second team's
never as good as the first.
[IN ENGLISH] Got a look at the directory.
That company moved out three months ago.
[IN SPANISH]
If they were ever there at all.
[IN ENGLISH] Quiet part of the city here.
Cartel keep Cali buttoned down?
Nobody talks.
All the multinationals
used to have offices here in Cali.
"Used to"?
Pulled out because of the city's ties
to the narcotics trade.
The Rodríguez brothers
are the only game in town now.
Fucking drug dealers
pretending to be stockbrokers.
Motherfuckers ruined this city.
[IN SPANISH] Where are we headed next?
[IN ENGLISH] Please.
This way, Mr. Starkman.
How the hell are you supposed
to fly international if you can't smoke?
I guess you can always quit.
And let United Airlines
tell me how to live?
Remind me again... Kansas City?
- Leavenworth.
- What the fuck for?
My father was in the army.
There's a base there.
They sent him to train.
I was like... seven years old.
What? It's America.
That's for sure.
So am I meeting the brothers at the hotel?
Yes.
Serious stones on these guys.
Retiring, like they run Lehman Brothers.
It's a good break for you, though.
You'll get immunity
when the surrender goes through.
I don't sell cocaine.
I don't shoot anyone.
You're a member of the Cali cartel.
You ever hear of conspiracy, amigo?
Relax. I got this. Look, they're lucky
to have us both, Jorge.
You can't put a price on freedom.
Though Lord knows I try.
[MIGUEL IN SPANISH]
I assume you would prefer U.S. currency?
[MEDINA] Of course.
[MIGUEL] Currency aside,
we aren't in the habit
of paying for things in advance.
What guarantee do we have
that you will provide what you promise?
Forgive my brother.
We are grateful for the support
you and your people have offered.
This afternoon, our associate,
Mr. Pallomari,
will prepare the contribution
and arrange delivery.
Very well.
The contribution should be divided
among seven men.
Their names are on the list.
All right, very well. Going forward,
I think it's best if Mr. Pallomari deals
with my colleague, Mr. Giraldo.
As you wish.
Have a great day, gentlemen.
Well, our surrender has been bought.
Now it must be paid for.
And they say we're the criminals.
Sons of bitches.
Small price to pay, brother,
for the rest of your life.
Gentlemen, I will prepare these payments
myself, as soon as I'm back in the office.
And I'll make sure
that all of this is in order.
Mr. Starkman is next, the lawyer.
[IN ENGLISH] If you ever make it to Miami
and you need a lawyer...
hit me up.
I wasn't planning on it,
but thank you, Mr. Starkman.
Yeah, nobody ever plans on it.
Mr. Starkman.
- Welcome to Cali.
- Yeah.
The Rodríguez brothers
are pleased to welcome you.
No offense,
but remind me again what you do?
I'm the chief accountant
to the Rodríguez brothers.
What happened to the other guy?
The good-looking one? Pacho?
Mr. Herrera?
Yeah, I bet he's the guy who's got
all the pussy in town on speed dial.
Yeah. Please, sir.
- Feistl.
- How's it going?
Well, slow so far,
but Calderón seems like good police.
Yeah. Good.
That journalist come through?
I'm on the money man right now.
- See where he takes me.
- Gracias.
Eyes open, Feistl.
- Everything by the book.
- Will do.
- Keep me posted.
- [CHRISTINA] Baby, wait.
I'm sorry.
Come here.
[ENGINE TURNS OVER]
[AMADO IN SPANISH]
The Arellano Felix brothers
are still wasting time with heroin.
Hey! What? You're not going to say hello?
- Hello.
- Are you in a bad mood or what?
Amado... this is the life.
You guys helped me.
I moved the last 100 tons
in less than 50 days.
You tell me if we're a great team or not.
[PACHO] That's why we're here.
Can you handle a bigger package?
I'm the Lord of the Skies, brother.
What do you think?
[PEÑA IN ENGLISH] Amado Carrillo Fuentes.
Leader of the Juárez cartel.
He was one of the most
enterprising traffickers in Mexico
and one of the first to get into business
with his Colombian friends to the south.
While Escobar saw
the Mexican traffickers as a threat,
Cali saw them as a partner.
A partner that shared over 1,900 miles
of virtually undefended border
with Cali's biggest customer:
the United States.
And right about the time
the Caribbean corridor closed
along came NAFTA, when the U.S.-Mexico
border was open for business.
And Amado took full advantage,
agreeing to ferry Cali cocaine
into the States.
They called it "the Mexican trampoline,"
bouncing cocaine into America,
and bouncing cash right back.
[IN SPANISH]
I can move however much you give me.
I just have two questions: How much?
And for how much longer, Pacho?
Because I know about your deal.
I know you want to turn yourselves in.
There is a deal on the table, Amado.
But we have six months
to turn ourselves in. That's the truth.
Until then,
we will honor our commitment to you.
Right, and after?
What happens after that?
The business will adjust.
This I know. It will always adjust.
This will never end.
There will be other partners
and more drugs. But what about you?
What will happen to you?
You can't tell me you're going to retire,
as if this was any normal business.
You know this is a way of life.
It retires you when it's done with you.
Or are you going to start playing golf
like an old man?
[SIGHS]
We need to count on you maintaining
the same terms on this last shipment.
Done.
It'll be my gift to the Gentlemen of Cali.
All right? But...
you have to come with me to Juárez.
- I want to show you something.
- What is it?
The future, Pacho.
The fucking future, that's all.
- Here's your passport.
- Thank you.
All right, and you board through Gate 15.
Okay.
- Have a great trip.
- Thank you.
Have a great day.
Next.
[IN ENGLISH] I'm going to Panama.
I need you to radio ahead
to the DEA office.
I'm afraid not. This plane can't take off.
New orders.
What are you talking about?
[MAN] I'm sorry, sir.
I'm not looking for that kind of trouble.
Oh, shit.
What the fuck is going on?
Orders are orders.
You heard the ambassador.
Our friends from the Senate here
want the down-low from a real-life hero.
Guess that's you.
You got somewhere better to be?
You wore the wrong shoes.
Fuck.
Is that the Río Negro?
[FEISTL] What do we got here?
The captain likes this one.
You won't find their name on the lease,
but the Rodríguez brothers
own the top six floors.
Oh, fuck. For real?
I told you,
there are some honest cops in Cali.
Let me reach out to men I trust.
Quietly. Keep an eye on this place.
You go back to Bogotá and...
get a warrant.
Come on, guys,
the place isn't moving anywhere.
Get that paper
and we'll turn this place upside down.
Why wait?
Judge in Bogotá signed a warrant for us
before we left.
Which you never told me about.
[IN SPANISH] This is the kind of bullshit
I don't like. Are you playing me or what?
[IN ENGLISH] Hey, man, it's like you said.
It's hard to know who to trust.
I wasn't even sure we were gonna need it.
There's no address on this warrant.
You said this place is connected,
so let's put in some work.
Do you know the kind of shit
I could land in?
Huh?
I don't have a DEA pension waiting for me.
Pensions aren't that great, to be honest.
Fuck.
Let's do it.
[IN SPANISH] I need a tactical team
sent to 15th Street and 4th Avenue, copy?
[DISPATCHER] Copy that.
Requesting a tactical team
at 15th Street and 4th Avenue.
[MIGUEL] You do realize, don't you,
after we surrender,
all of this shit will end.
No more sitting by the pool,
smoking your cigar,
telling everyone what to do.
Look, Miguel,
I'm tired of telling people what to do.
And no one has ever listened to you.
What's the difference?
But you know what?
Never, in human history, have two brothers
accomplished what we have.
We aren't the first people in history
to build an empire, Gilberto.
But we're the first to retire
leaving the empire intact.
If Mom were alive, she'd be proud.
Brothers are well, nephews are well,
sons are well.
[ENRIQUE OVER RADIO]
Boss, we just heard a call
that a tactical team left Jamundí station
heading to 4th Avenue.
Enrique, where are you?
Watching our visitors from the DEA.
They've been checking addresses
all over town.
But right now, they're stopped,
just doing nothing.
Yes, but where are you?
At 15th Street and... 4th. On 4th Avenue.
Enrique, fuck!
There's a police convoy coming at you!
Get Pallomari out of there now!
[PHONE RINGING]
Answer, you bastard, answer.
- Hello? What's up?
- Listen, it's Salcedo.
You're going to have unwelcome guests.
Leave now.
I don't have time for this.
I'm supervising an important project.
That's exactly why I need you to get out.
Just because you say so?
I know you're arranging an important
transaction for the bosses this afternoon.
Listen, this is none of your business.
I'll bet your desk is covered
with American dollars.
Look, Guillermo, please.
You've got papers. You've got names.
You've got things that shouldn't be seen.
- Jorge...
- Get out of there!
You do your job and I'll do mine.
This is my job! I'm telling you...
Son of a bitch!
[PHONE RINGING]
Fuck your mother.
I need you to check the paper shredders
and the floppy disks
still in the computers.
Invoices. Bills of lading.
Anything on the computers.
- [IN ENGLISH] Warrant says paper only.
- Yeah? Warrants say a lot of things.
[IN SPANISH] Let's go.
[IN ENGLISH] At least
someone's willing to get wet.
Don't worry, you'll be back
in Intelligence Group soon enough.
It's not...
This is a waste of our time, Chris.
And more importantly,
this is a waste of a warrant.
You know what?
Andrew Jackson here says all we find
in this fucking high rise
- is a nice view of the city.
- All right.
Well, I got... whoever this guy is
and he says otherwise.
[PHONE RINGING]
[IN SPANISH] Fucking shit!
[IN SPANISH]
Gentlemen, how may I help you?
Seventh floor. Mr. Pallomari's office.
I'll let them know you're here
so you can head up.
Oh, oh, oh...
People love surprises.
Gentlemen, you can't...
You. What the fuck
are you still doing here?
What the fuck am I doing? My job.
We told your associate the same thing.
Sorry, boss, I tried, but he won't listen.
- You go get the car.
- Please get out.
- I have to finish. Fuck your mother.
- The back stairs.
- Yes, sir.
- Finish what?
My job, Jorge.
No. Please, we have to get rid
of all of that now.
We aren't arguing.
You aren't touching anything.
I've got a method and a system.
- Method and a system?
- Yes, sir.
Yes? What you've got is ten years of jail
time sitting on your desk, you idiot.
- Get out.
- No.
[CALDERÓN]
Attention! Colombian National Police!
Where are the files?
Get to work. Let's go!
This is an office.
We're working. How can I help you?
We need access to your files, invoices,
and all of your correspondence.
Ah...
If that's the case,
I need to see a warrant.
Are you supposed to be in charge?
Well, yes, I'm in charge.
Come on.
Good morning.
I have to see every invoice you have.
Hey!
This says documents only.
Fuck your mother.
[IN ENGLISH] Could you repeat that, sir?
My Spanish is... is a bit rough.
[IN SPANISH] You didn't get that?
[IN ENGLISH] Only papers.
[IN SPANISH] Documents only.
- [IN ENGLISH] All right.
- Claudia.
[IN SPANISH] Keep an eye on the things
they're taking. Now!
Yes, sir.
Leave it. Let it be.
Chivo, check everything
and make an inventory, all right?
[IN ENGLISH] Hey, I like presents.
What'd you get us?
[IN SPANISH] That's private.
Ignacio, please show the gentleman
last year's documents.
This way, please.
[IN ENGLISH] Excuse me, sir.
[IN SPANISH] I must insist.
[IN ENGLISH] Your phone's off the hook.
[IN SPANISH] Do you have a bill of lading?
Yes? Let me see.
More? Everything.
- Just these?
- And copies below.
- These as well, no?
- Yes, sir.
- All right. '93. Yeah?
- Those are the most recent.
Grab that.
[IN ENGLISH]
Looks like you owe me that 20.
Oh, yeah.
You were right.
[STECHNER] This area saw the biggest spike
in trafficking after Escobar was killed.
Can't we just spray chemicals
on this place and be done with it?
Unfortunately, agricultural concerns
in the region won't allow it.
That's right.
Chiquita Bananas is down here.
I know those guys. Big contributors.
Okay. Here we are.
Jesus H. Christ.
Must've been one hell of a firefight, huh?
No doubt, sir.
- Gentlemen, this is Captain Mills.
- Captain.
- Our advisor on this mission down here.
- How you doing, sir?
He liaised with a team
of Colombian commandos on this raid here.
These guys FARC or traffickers?
[STECHNER] Both.
Probably started out doing security
for the traffickers, or extorting them.
FARC wants to overthrow the government.
Cocaine finances their struggles.
Top of the line.
There's an arms race going on down here.
And this shit...
is jet fuel.
You guys ready for lunch?
[SENATOR TOYLE] Lunch?
Yeah. Sure. Why not?
Go. Go. Go.
[IN SPANISH] This 24-hour party thing...
is tiring after a couple of days.
Can you imagine if it was your life?
What's on your mind?
Dad, and the last thing he said to me.
What? "Get the fuck out"?
No.
He said... that in this world...
there was no place for a man like me.
I made a place for myself.
I proved him wrong.
And now, I have to give it all up.
What kind of man would I be
if I gave it all up?
I don't know, brother.
But what I do know is that you have
a couple billion dollars...
and the rest of your life
to figure it out.
[GERDA] What are they giving me?
What do you mean,
"What are they giving you?"
They took my son, didn't they?
They have to give us something.
Have they offered you something?
An apartment.
Accept it.
Afterwards, I'll sell it for cash.
We'll take their money now.
Later, we'll take vengeance.
- Do it, then get back up here.
- Can you wake Pedro up?
- I want to speak with him.
- Don't worry about Pedro. He's sleeping.
[DIAL TONE]
I heard we cut it close today.
I thought they didn't have a warrant.
That's what I was told
by our friend on the force.
A few more seconds
and we'd have had real trouble.
Those new DEA guys
are sharper than they look.
Well, luckily, we have you.
Did they get anything?
Some files.
So nothing. Good.
I'll take care of the rest today.
That thing you've got tonight with Paola,
enjoy yourself. Go on.
[VAN NESS IN ENGLISH] We got names,
addresses. These files are legit.
How are you guys?
Captain.
We'll catalog and seal
the ones from today.
If you could help us with transport...
Okay... there must be a misunderstanding.
The files stay here.
We need to sort through these.
As you can see,
we know how to process evidence, Feistl.
- That wasn't the deal. This was our intel.
- It was a CNP operation.
We let you join, support.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- No, I'm not.
I'm not.
[IN SPANISH] But anything we find
we'll be sure to share with you.
I was instructed
you should be back in Bogotá tonight.
You're going out on the last flight.
[FEISTL SIGHS]
[IN ENGLISH] He burned us.
Who's that, Chris?
The last honest cop in Cali?
No, man. He clowned me, too.
I'm calling the boss.
[PHONE RINGING]
- [PHONE BEEPS]
- Fuck!
[MILLS] Those things
ain't going 25 feet down here.
Thanks. Hey, you DOD?
So they say. But I still ID as a Marine.
I'm part
of the military assistance package.
- CIA?
- Oh, shit. Fuck, no.
Can I get a smoke?
Thanks.
Where you from?
The last place? Pendleton.
I was out there teaching Saudi soldiers
how to do jumping jacks.
That shit's a lot harder than it sounds.
- So is it really that bad down here?
- Yeah. It is.
You got paramilitary, FARC,
traffickers, us.
Some pretty hairy bullshit down here.
Right, but not hairy enough
for the truth to make its case.
Magazines on those bodies
are 7.62 millimeter.
They go in an AK-47, right?
Those guns, the fancy ones,
they chamber in a 5.56.
This whole thing is staged.
Those are run-of-the-mill guerrillas.
Peasants, not traffickers.
[STECHNER] You know your guns.
I'm gonna head on down.
Not very original, Stechner.
Even for the CIA.
Yeah, well, sometimes you need
to make the truth a little more... plain.
Well, how's this for truth?
They go home and tell everyone
the war on drugs is a fucking stage show.
And all the money they put in
is pissed away.
Even the hero said it's fucked up.
What's that do to your plan?
[SENATOR TOYLE]
I'm gonna level with you.
Sending a five-billion-dollar aid package
to a country that's on the verge
of becoming a narco-democracy,
that's a bad look in the Senate.
All due respect, Senator, you're looking
at a petri dish for the next Castro,
and this one's fed by narco dollars.
And not just here. Venezuela, Honduras.
Rich dictators
with anti-American hard-ons.
We turn our back on this place,
it all goes to hell.
Colombia is perfectly situated to help us
in both Central and South America.
The right American footprint here,
Black Hawks, small arms,
night vision, advisors like Mills...
we help secure a stable Colombia,
and it becomes a beacon for the region.
[SENATOR TOYLE] Well, if you want
the American people
to get behind sending
billions of dollars to Colombia...
we need
a no-fucking-around victory down here.
Look, gentlemen, the Colombian government
is months away from dismantling one
of the biggest drug cartels in history.
And they will do it without firing a shot.
No body count, no dirty hands.
I can't imagine the folks back home
won't like that.
Agent Peña.
What do you think?
Is it true? Is a big win coming?
Agent Stechner and I...
we have a long-standing difference
of opinion on just about everything.
But he and I can both agree...
a big win is coming.
Glad we're on the same page, Agent Peña.
So the whole surrender plan
is about fucking fundraising!
The Colombians get a check and you get
to play army men in the jungle?
I'm thinking about the next battle,
the one that really counts.
Which means you're willing
to lose this one!
The drug war?
Oh, come on, man! We lost it!
You were there!
Ever stop and think that anyone
that takes this as personally as you do
is doing it wrong?
- Fuck you!
- Yeah.
See ya!
[IN SPANISH] Where are they now?
[CALDERÓN]
I just put them on a plane to Bogotá.
- And the files?
- We've got them.
Are you sure?
Look, they tricked me
with that fucking warrant, all right?
And I couldn't warn you because we were
all together like a fucking family.
These Americans know what they're doing.
They aren't fucking idiots.
[IN ENGLISH]
I ever tell you I did a rotation in Chile?
No, Dan, you never told me
you did a rotation in fucking Chile.
The accountant.
- You clock his accent?
- No.
A little off. You know, he said something:
"Concha su madre."
Okay, what's that?
"Fuck your mother" or something?
Exactly.
But then he said another word:"Cachai."
It's a phrase that they typically
only use in Chile.
And if he's from Chile...
He can be extradited.
[STODDARD]
Panama DEA said no warrant, no detention.
- Fuck.
- Plus, Jurado didn't stay in Panama.
They know where he went?
No.
So Jurado could be anywhere. Fuck!
Also, boss, Feistl and Van Ness
have been trying you. A lot.
All right, well, put them through
when you get them. I'm on my way back.
- And Stoddard?
- Yeah, boss?
Jurado has a wife in Bogotá.
She's American.
Put a tap on her phone.
- I don't think I can do that.
- Just do it.
[IN SPANISH] Well, the truth is, we're
very interested in your proposal, Jorge.
And in your potential for growth.
You've exceeded Paola's description,
which wasn't easy.
Of course, we were inconvenienced
by the six-month delay, which...
took us by surprise.
I take my commitments very seriously,
gentlemen.
And I couldn't leave without ensuring
my replacement met the standard
they've come to expect.
[DAVID] Go wait for him over there.
- Good evening. How are you?
- Good, thank you.
[INVESTOR] Well, I think that merits
another bottle of wine, no?
Yes.
Look at that son of a bitch.
Thinks his shit doesn't stink, or what?
Thank you.
So, a security expert married to a rising
star in one of Cali's top law firms.
Have you worked together before?
My compliments.
David Rodríguez.
How are you?
Don't let the elegant suit fool you.
This guy's a real son of a bitch.
Seriously.
In fact, he's one of our best men.
You see?
Enjoy it.
Ma'am.
You... Where do you know him from?
Is he a friend of yours?
You know Cali is a very small city.
Even more so
when one is in the security business.
One must deal with all sorts of people.
Is that the paperwork
I'm supposed to deliver?
These documents are very sensitive.
And I don't feel comfortable
transferring possession to anyone else.
All right. Let's go, then.
Open the door, Córdova.
Go fuck yourself, Pallomari.
- Huh?
- In the front seat.
What the fuck's wrong with you?
Open the door. Fuck your mother.
In the front.
I'm not your fucking employee.
[IN ENGLISH]
Making friends everywhere he goes.
No shit.
Look at this fucking neighborhood.
This guy's doing more than filing W-9s.
Es el cabrón.
The fucking man.
[IN SPANISH] I haven't been able
to reach an agreement.
He's very stubborn.
[GILBERTO] Listen to me, Pacho.
We have to seal the deal.
It's very important.
Amado has to go to Juárez tomorrow.
I'll go with him and close the deal.
All right. Keep me informed.
Good night.
Good night, Gilberto.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Compliments of Mr. Carrillo.
["SWEET HARMONY" PLAYING]
♪ Play a part ♪
♪ In a greater scheme ♪
♪ Try to live the dream ♪
♪ On a wider scene ♪
♪ Let's come together ♪
♪ Right now ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ In sweet harmony ♪
♪ Let's come together ♪
♪ Right now ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ In sweet harmony ♪
♪ Let's come together ♪
It's been a long time
since anyone asked me on a date.
Come in, please.
Take a seat.
Sir... your offer of this apartment
is very generous.
But?
But... I would like to know the terms.
The terms?
How often will you come here to visit me?
As often as you like.
Or never.
This is your home.
Is there a monthly stipend?
A stipend?
Mr. Rodríguez, I married Claudio Salazar
when I was 18 years old.
I knew nothing.
Now I need to get away from his family,
and I need my son back.
If you could help me with that...
I can.
Then I accept.
It's great to hear that.
Why don't you get some rest?
Eat something.
Tomorrow morning, I'll send for your son.
How does that sound?
Good.
Take a seat.
[IN ENGLISH] Fifty miles an hour,
you could jump into water and survive.
- You can't leave her on the bus.
- I guess you do. You leave her on the bus.
No.
- I would leave her.
- You would leave her?
- [DOOR OPENING]
- Shh...
All right. Here we go.
Dan.
Is that who I think it is?
Gilberto fucking Rodríguez.
Fuck.
Oh, my fucking God. Okay.
[PHONE RINGS]
- Peña.
- Boss, it's Feistl.
- Where the fuck have you been?
- Sir, I got eyes on Gilberto Rodríguez.
- You're looking at him right now?
- Yes.
Just say the word
and we can take him down.
What's the move, boss?
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[IN SPANISH] Sorry to interrupt.
[IN ENGLISH]
You want to go after Gilberto Rodríguez?
["SOBRE LAS OLAS" PLAYING]