We're in the car, honey.
We're going to
the hospital for tests.
We're in the hospital.
We're going
to the Doctor's office.
Yeah.
Can you tell me
what this is called?
Uh, you use it to get
food from inside.
Yes, but what's
it called?
Is it a spatula?
- No.
- Good.
Is it a can opener?
Uh, no, it's, um...
It's, um...
You're trying
to make me look stupid.
You can go to hell!
Why don't you
kill yourself?
Andres.
It's okay.
There she is.
Here I am.
Here, come on.
You just need to answer
a few more questions.
Then we're going home.
We'll have lunch, okay?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I have Alzheimer's.
I know.
The mood swings come on
quickly, but, um...
It's under control.
Don't worry. He's actually
perfect for the drug trial.
Oh.
Thank God.
We can start
as soon as next week.
Andres...
Oh, my God!
♪ House 8x09 ♪
Better Half
Original air date on January 23, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
[Massive Attack's Teardrop]
♪
Early onset
familial Alzheimer's.
Brazilian descent.
Blood chemistry
showed high ammonia.
Vomiting stopped after the E.R.
put him on antiemetics.
Any recent
health issues?
Just a sore throat
a few weeks ago.
How advanced is he?
Could be
hyperalimentation.
Advanced enough,
but no IV feedings.
The wife shut down
a floral company
to stay home
and feed him
every meal he's had
in the last four years.
Do we owe this case
to your guilt
at having ignored
your own forgetful mommy?
My guilt over my mom is why
I put up with my dad.
You're taking this case
because we're running
a phase-two trial
on an Alzheimer's drug.
You couldn't round up enough
doddering old Guinea pigs.
You need us to fix
this little piggy?
I'd like to sit in.
Especially since you're
short a team member.
You mean Taub?
Got him in here.
He asked for a personal day.
His daughter's sick.
Isn't that the point
of having a spare?
I denied his request.
After I'd already
approved it,
which you knew
because I sent you a memo.
Dr. Adams...
Taped under your chair
is an index card.
Would you read it, please?
"Wednesday, 2:43 p.m.,
"a black Pawn will believe
he's the black King
"and attempt
to capture the...
white head of diagnostics."
- It's 10:15 on Friday.
- Damn it.
Look, the point is
I saw this coming.
Dr. Foreman and I did not
always see eye-to-eye.
But he never had the power
to overrule me.
Now that he has the power,
he won't be able
to resist the temptation
to use it.
With great power
comes great micromanaging.
And great vests.
I know you're
the better diagnostician.
I'm not gonna interfere.
I'm only here to help.
Could be transient nitrogen load
from a G.I. bleed.
Not if the vomiting's
persistent.
Which we won't know, because
the E.R. put him on antiemetics.
Take him off.
Wait. He's puking his guts out.
We'd risk aspiration.
I'm just disagreeing,
not overruling.
So glad you're on board.
Take him off antiemetics,
do an upper endoscopy
to check for bleeds.
It could be
a bladder infection.
We'll run
a pregnancy test.
Oh, I'm not pregnant.
Any type of birth control
can fail.
Not mine.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You said you were married.
Yeah, happily.
That's okay.
Sex can wane in any
marriage over time.
No, no.
We've never had sex.
Oh, we kiss and cuddle,
but neither one of us
is interested in sex.
You're...both celibate.
No, neither of us.
Celibacy is a choice.
This is our orientation.
We're asexual.
Not quite sure
what box to check here.
You're making a mistake.
If I had the power
to veto him,
given all the crap I've
put up with over the years,
don't know if I could
use it objectively.
I do, I can, I have.
Might be easier if you'd
stay out of the room.
I thought
it'd be different.
This week.
Supposed to talk
to his P.O.
about getting his
ankle monitor off early.
You're saying he should
defer to you?
No, I'm just saying what he's
doing doesn't seem rational,
which makes me think
it's rational
in a way
I'm not privy to.
He always has a plan.
And he's always
self-destructive.
He may just be shooting
himself in the ankle.
I know it feels strange.
Dr. Chase is just
looking in your throat.
We're in the hospital.
You're fine.
That's a pretty nice
trophy, there, Andres.
He coached youth soccer.
Took a team that was 0-6
all the way to the state finals
at Long Branch.
Hey, thanks for
doing this in here.
Switching rooms
can be very disorienting.
You take very good
care of him.
I love him.
Sickness and health, right?
Upper esophagus
is clear.
Moving on to
the G.E. junction.
Hi.
- Hey.
- I'm sorry.
Family members only
during procedures.
Uh, I'll--
I'll be outside.
Oh, no. Please, um,
it's okay.
Joseph helps me
with my husband sometimes.
He's a good friend.
Which means not family.
Wait, we're gonna
be here a while.
Why don't you show Joseph
where the visitor's lounge is?
Okay.
What?
Surprised you didn't
go into the diplomatic corps.
Oh, you think
they're...
No, if they're having sex, it's
probably with their genitals.
Mallory-Weiss tear.
Vomiting must have
torn the lining.
You know that close to
1% of the population
identifies as asexual?
We really gotta
get you laid.
If I have to plough
that furrow myself, so be it.
I have a patient
who's asexual.
Is she a giant pool
of algae?
It's a valid
sexual orientation.
According to this
article, at least.
Yeah, I think
I read that too.
Is that
fugliness weekly?
She's perfectly
fine-looking.
Happily married
for ten years.
To a guy who loves penis
enough for the both of them.
He's asexual too.
Ran a complete
physical on her.
Nothing wrong except
a common bladder infection.
100 bucks says I can
find a medical reason
why she doesn't
want to have sex.
You're out of your mind
if you think I'm letting you
anywhere near my patient.
Fine.
I won't go near her.
Just give me her file
and any blood samples
you have left over.
No contact, whatsoever.
You talk to her,
the bet is void.
No contact.
Plays to my
strengths anyway.
Right now's not
a good time, House.
Not for the Dean
of Medicine.
But it's a perfect time
if you're a member of my team.
Which one are you?
What did
the endoscopy show?
No signs of ulcers
or blockages.
But you found a tear
just below the esophagus.
Explains the bleeding.
Doesn't explain why he vomited
so hard he ripped his insides.
His liver enzymes
are slightly elevated.
Gallstones could've--
no complaints of pain.
Steatohepatitis would make his
AST and ATL levels rise.
Are you calling
his liver fat?
Start the patient on statins,
and do a biopsy to confirm.
And knock him out.
I've heard he's a wiggler.
There's no need
to put him under.
We can confirm fatty liver
with an ultrasound.
Just making
an observation.
Well done.
Now, as a member
of my team,
you can make the equally-useful
observations
that the sky is blue,
I'm wearing pants,
and I'm ignoring
your first observation.
Of course.
Wait.
And there it is.
You're trying to screw
with my confidence.
Well, if I wanted
to do that,
I'd tell you how much
the nurses hate you.
You're trying to get me to
define myself as a subordinate
to keep me from
ever intervening,
even if it's fully
in the scope of my duties.
Like now.
This isn't
about diagnostics,
it's about what's safe
for the patient.
Do the ultrasound.
Ultrasound it is.
And the nurses love you.
You don't think I knew
House was gonna tell you
to ignore me and not
do the ultrasound?
This is an
ultrasound machine.
Which you're gonna use to do
an ultrasound-guided biopsy.
Probably got a kit
stashed here...
"Cuddy dark
will waste his afternoon
chasing
conspiracy theories."
You're letting him
get inside your head.
He could do a lot
of damage in there.
Dr. Chase.
He started
vomiting again.
This is why we stopped
the antiemetics.
We needed to see if
it was still a symptom.
Okay.
Here, you want this?
Get your hands off me.
You're taking my head.
It's okay, Andres.
You're in the hospital.
Here.
- 10 milligrams of Diazepam!
- Already on it.
I'm fine.
I'm all right.
Foreman.
Blood in his urine.
Resume the antiemetics,
and increase the sedation.
He really went after her.
Maybe he found out
about her "good friend."
It was just paranoid rage,
typical of Alzheimer's.
We don't even know if they
were sleeping together.
A few hours ago
you were sure.
And that's
significant why?
Sorry. Only the bleeding's
medically relevant.
No, I wasn't
being rhetorical.
If they are
sleeping together,
why do we disapprove?
You're pro-infidelity?
She's not married.
If marriage is feeding
and cleaning someone,
limiting conversations, to
repeating a few simple commands,
then I was married
to my pet rat.
And a lot of people
owe me wedding gifts.
And we're walking,
we're walking.
I don't care how sick
your spouse gets,
you don't jump ship.
Alzheimer's
is different.
She can't share
her problems with him,
or plan for the future.
The man she married
no longer exists.
Yes, he does.
He's in there.
This is why
you get married.
Said the divorced woman
to the divorced man.
I didn't jump ship.
My husband sank it
when he cheated on me.
Commitment's
not conditional.
She is there for him in the only
way that matters now.
She gave up her life
to take care of him.
Which proves
she's an idiot.
If she had any sense, she'd have
stuck him in a facility
and jumped
on that strange--
Dr. Foreman.
We were just
looking for you.
I was right about
the antiemetics.
If you kept him
on them like I said,
he wouldn't have gotten agitated
and punched his wife.
Yes, we're back to my
supposed diabolical plan
to shake your confidence.
Let's see if this helps.
If you're speaking
as a team member,
then I'd say
you're a moron.
Because taking him
off the antiemetics
gave us crucial
diagnostic information.
If you're speaking
as Dean of Medicine,
then I'd say
you're a moron.
'Cause your micromanaging
kept us from doing a biopsy.
If we had, the patient
would have been anesthetized
hours ago, thus unable to go
all Chris Brown on her ass.
Unless one of your index cards
actually predicted the guy
was gonna punch his wife,
everything you're saying
is post hoc rationalization.
Dr. Park,
would you please
reach under that chair?
"The patient will
punch his wife."
You clearly wrote that
after the fact.
Dr. Adams,
would you please
reach into my pants?
"Dr. Blackenshmurtz
will accuse me of writing
about the punch after the fact."
Now, look.
Here's a photograph
of me holding a newspaper.
Dated last Tuesday.
Now, how could I have
gotten my hands on that?
You done?
Rhabdomyolysis
fits the vomiting,
pigmenturia,
and renal failure.
No muscle symptoms,
and urine had no myoglobin.
TTP fits, though.
Start him
on plasmapheresis.
Unless...
Unless I need to say,
"mother, may I?"
And mother
is an abbreviation.
Fresh plasma will replace
the damaged red blood cells
that are clogging
his kidneys.
That sounds hopeful.
How is that feeling?
I've never been hit
in the eye before.
I feel kinda badass.
I think maybe
you should go.
I'm fine. Okay?
See you tomorrow.
Okay.
We're not
having an affair.
It's none
of my business.
I mean, not--
not really.
'Cause nothing's happened.
We've talked
about it a lot, and...
It's just really hard
doing this by myself.
When's the last time you had
a full night's sleep?
Um...
I don't know.
Three years.
You're not going to
get any rest here.
People who are sick
are not the only ones
who need to be
taken care of.
Why doesn't Chase
have to be here?
You think he knows
anything about women
who don't want
to have sex?
Hormone levels
are normal.
This woman seems
perfectly healthy.
What does it matter
if she says she's asexual?
It's the fundamental drive
of our species.
Sex is healthy.
Orgasms oxygenate
the brain,
lighting up over
30 different areas
and making us forget
how boring Susie Cooper is.
That last one may not
be universal.
How about damage
to her spinal cord
blocking the signals
from her genitals?
Sex drive is in the brain.
I suppose it could be
psychological intimacy issues
caused by childhood abuse.
She's been sharing a toilet
with the same guy
for the last ten years.
That's not the same.
Sex releases oxytocin.
It's the neurochemical basis
for bonding.
And that's why men
always marry their right hands.
It's different for girls.
No it's not.
I've tapped over 30 guys
and never wanted to see
most of them again.
I live next to
a Jewish frat.
We are veering wildly off track.
Please continue.
This woman's life is probably
better off without sex.
Eliminates most
of her insecurity,
she's immune
to most advertising
and can have honest
relationships with men.
Not a lot of them.
We've run every test
and ruled out all the options.
You're gonna have to accept
she just doesn't want sex.
Lots of people
don't have sex.
The only people
who don't want it
are either sick,
dead, or lying.
So maybe she's lying.
You think she's had
a boyfriend on the side?
For ten years?
Sticking around the whole time?
Doesn't make sense.
What does...
30?
Everybody lies.
Higher or lower?
Followed your advice
and took the night off.
Seems to have
done you some good.
Mm-Hmm.
Where's my husband?
He's not in the hospital.
So he just walked out?
All of the shift nurses
had their hands full
with a double code.
Perfectly reasonable explanation.
Same thing happened to me.
Couldn't find my keys for days.
The police
have been notified.
I have staff searching.
You told me
it was okay to leave.
I'm sorry.
He has Alzheimer's!
It's freezing outside,
and he's sick!
I mean, you don't even know
what it is yet, do you?
The plasmapheresis
hasn't had time to work,
but TTP is our
most likely--
Okay, I'm just--
I have to go look for him.
Hey, don't be an ass.
Can't you see
she's upset?
No, she's guilty.
'Cause instead of being
at her husband's side,
she was under you.
Okay, that's--y--
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
He already said
I was an ass.
Personally, I applaud
your decision
to step down off your cross
and get on with your life,
but your misplaced guilt
is shutting down your brain.
We need you to sit, focus,
and answer our questions.
So, at 6:00 a.m.,
the patient wakes up,
and the first thing
he sees...
In moments of confusion,
Alzheimer's patients
regress to old routines.
So what would your husband do
on a Saturday morning?
Nothing. Be at home.
What about a year ago?
Or five years? Ten?
I don't know, um, he...
He trained
for a marathon once.
Soccer practice.
We took a cooking class.
That soccer trophy
you were telling me about.
It's gone.
Where was practice?
It was close to here.
On Chesterfield.
Okay, he comes, he thinks
he's waiting for practice.
He'd want to get out
of the wind.
What's somewhere he could
see the kids arrive?
There.
Over here.
On three.
One, two, three.
Nothing.
Not dead until
he's warm and dead.
Get him to the ICU.
Start him on
extracorporeal circulation.
That'll raise his
temperature too quickly,
it'll cause acidosis.
We can deal with
his metabolism crashing,
we can't reverse brain damage
if we go too slowly.
Either way, we don't get his
temperature above 95,
it's not going to matter.
Multiple warm lavage
is safer.
Do what House says.
He has no heartbeat,
and he's not breathing.
How can he not be dead?
The body slows down
when it cools,
but it doesn't fully stop.
We're warming his blood
outside of his body,
then putting it back.
It'll raise his
temperature enough
that his heart should
naturally start.
Then we can shock it
back into rhythm.
And if it doesn't start?
Then there's
nothing we can do.
You think it's possible
he knew what he was doing?
Like some part of him gets what
he's putting his wife through,
so he tried to--
kill himself?
It's what I'd do
if I were him.
At least I wish I would.
I meant run away.
You think you should
kill yourself
if you become a burden
to the people who love you?
If you really
love them back, then...
Yes.
That's really dark.
It's not naive.
I just believe
people are capable
of more than you do,
apparently.
We've got brain activity.
Temp's at 93.
His heart should
start soon.
My dad left me alone
to care for my alcoholic mom
and raise my baby sister.
I was just a teenager.
I spent half my time
changing diapers
and the other half
cleaning up my mom's vomit.
But it must've
been important
that you stayed
for both of them.
Mom died after
a few years.
It was ugly and painful,
and she went with me hating her.
My sister ended up drinking
half of her life away
and hating me because
I couldn't help.
After mom,
I had nothing left.
So do I wish mom had used
a gun instead of a bottle?
Yes.
I--I didn't know.
That's why I told you.
Ventricular fibrillation.
300 milligrams
amiodarone.
Careful.
Once we establish rhythm,
any accidental movement
could crash him back into V-fib.
Clear.
We still have
a long way to go.
Cold can be protective
to the brain,
but there is
a possibility of damage.
We also need
to confirm and treat
whatever's
making him sick.
I just gotta do
a standard battery of tests.
Blood, urine, eeg...
Is that really necessary
for a free flu shot?
Excuse me.
I have to deal with someone
who's having a panic attack.
I specifically said
the bet was off if you
contacted the patient.
Exactly.
Never said anything
about the patient's husband.
The deal was a medical reason
why she doesn't have sex.
I admit I was stuck,
until I realized the medical
issue was not hers but his.
She's lying
to compensate.
It's a tale
as old as time.
Boy meets girl,
girl falls for boy,
boy says, "I'm asexual."
Girl says, "yeah, me too."
Your twisted logic
can't hide the fact
that tricking a patient
into being tested
is completely
unethical.
Come on.
Don't you think she deserves
to know why her husband
won't bend her over
the kitchen counter?
You love all that
caring crap.
You're not doing this out of
the kindness of your heart.
You're not even doing this
out of medical curiosity.
I thought I made it clear
I'm doing it for the cash.
Two people are happy,
and your natural impulse
is to destroy it.
How do you know
she's happy?
Did she tell you?
No, chirping birds flew out
of her butt carrying a banner.
All right, I admit
that my natural impulse
is to doubt peoples'
claims to happiness,
but yours is to be
a sucker for them.
You tell me
which one's worse.
He just opened his eyes
a little while ago.
His heartbeat's doing well,
and his body temperature
is stabilized.
There he is.
Me sinto quente.
Is that Portuguese?
Yeah.
Honey, I don't
understand.
Me sinto quente.
What's he saying?
I don't know.
I tried to learn
when we got married,
but I just--
it's okay. It's okay.
His body temperature
is rising.
It's above normal.
Wait, I thought--
I thought you said
it was stable.
Why is it still rising?
I don't know.
Vomiting, liver,
kidneys, and now fever.
I don't want to tell you
how to do your job, Dr. Foreman,
since telling people
how to do their job is your job,
but when your
less-than-competent
administration of this hospital
affects what's written
on my whiteboard...
Get to the point.
The word "fever."
Could come from
the patient's illness,
or it could come from the fact
that you allowed him
to saunter out of your hospital
and take a nap in the snow.
Couldn't have caught a virus
while he was outside.
Fever came on too fast.
The hypothermia could've
caused cell necrosis.
TTP was the diagnosis
when he walked out.
Fever's a little high,
but it still fits.
We should continue
plasmapheresis.
We're missing symptoms.
We should add language loss
and aggression.
Should we also
add forgetfulness?
- He's got Alzheimer's.
- We've just been assuming.
Because the patient's wife
said he exhibited
both for a year.
He's never hit her before
or lost all his English.
We have to consider
any change
since he's been admitted
as relevant.
Have to?
Do I need to pull out
another card?
Disseminated viral infection
with encephalitis.
Patient complained of
a sore throat a few weeks ago.
Start him on Interferon.
Encephalitis makes
his brain swell,
which causes symptoms
that are
hard to distinguish
from his Alzheimer's.
With the Interferon
his English should come back,
and the aggression
should subside.
But you're not sure.
Unfortunately, no.
And you're not sure if he has
brain damage from being frozen.
So best-case scenario,
I've just had a glimpse
into his future?
I can't take care
of him anymore.
Chances are his mental state
will improve.
You could get
more time with him.
We married six months
after I met him.
A year after that,
he started forgetting things.
I've known my husband
longer with his Alzheimer's
than without.
I've watched
more of him disappear
than I ever got to know.
I just can't
do this anymore.
You lose.
Blood work shows
high levels of prolactin.
Add that to some peripheral
red-green confusion,
puts my money--
excuse me, your money--
soon to be my money
on a tumor
near his pituitary.
Probably started growing
in his early teens.
Lowering his libido
and causing
erectile dysfunction.
A year on
dopamine agonists,
and he'll be a sex-crazed creep
just like the rest of us,
completely fascinated
by Susie Cooper.
I'd prefer to be paid
in a single $100 bill.
Always wanted to use one
to light a cigar.
Hooray for us.
We disproved his asexuality.
We also probably
ruined his life.
He'll thank us.
Then he'll doze off,
and then in a couple hours,
he'll thank us again.
It could destroy
his identity.
It's like a gay person being
told they're really straight.
So don't tell him.
Yeah, why bother
telling a guy
he has a tumor
growing in his head?
He'll notice it eventually, when
it starts leaking out his ears.
It's a slow-growing tumor.
He'll probably die
of boredom long before that.
You always do this.
You--you meddle
and force me into
impossible situations.
You knew the second
you told me about this case
that I'd get involved.
You wanted me to meddle.
Because no matter
how much you wanted
to believe in this
chaste romance,
you didn't
buy it either.
Where's that petition
House's P.O. sent over
about getting his
ankle monitor off?
On your desk.
You played me.
This whole thing was about
your ankle monitor.
You weren't trying
to undermine my confidence,
you were trying
to inflate it.
You manufactured
conflict with me
so eventually
you could let me win.
You knew it was encephalitis,
but you waited for me to say it
because then
with my ego boosted,
you thought I'd be in the mood
to take off your monitor
because I'd think
I could control you.
You're right.
Take off my monitor.
See, the beauty
of the plan
is that if it works,
you think you can control me.
If it fails, then you will
actually have proven
that you can control me.
It's pretty genius.
These are your
training wheels.
If you think
you're up to this job,
it's time to lose them.
Second half of my plan
might need work.
V-fib. Two rounds of 360
without establishing a rhythm.
Wait, Dr. Foreman!
Clear.
He's back.
I sure hope this
Alzheimer's drug trial
is worth a lot
to this hospital,
'cause we're wasting a crap-load
of time and manpower
just to let this guy
watch his mind shrivel
and keep his wife
miserable.
Heart attack
while he was on Interferon
rules out encephalitis,
but I still think I'm right
about the neural symptoms.
It's probably
aseptic meningitis.
Would have seen
meningial signs.
Given his abnormal
mental status, not necessarily.
Dr. Foreman,
would you please
reach under your chair?
There's just wet gum under here.
Where's the card?
What card?
I'm happy to leave
if you have
a better theory
than aseptic meningitis.
Toxins.
This guy went
on walkabout.
Chances are
he's done it before.
Wife keeps the doors
on the house locked.
Plenty of nasty stuff
to get into
during the middle
of the night.
We asked about toxins
on the history.
The wife said she was
sure to clear the house
for her husband's safety.
I'm sure she succeeded.
She's a PhD
in toxicology, right?
She's an ex-florist.
Search the home
for toxic plants,
methyl bromide,
any medications.
Stop.
You're not infallible. You were
wrong about encephalitis.
Just before you were.
Run CSF tests.
Find out what's
causing the meningitis.
You said you weren't gonna
overrule me diagnostically.
And you said I wouldn't
be able to help it.
Apparently, you were
right about that one.
Fine.
I'll look
for toxins myself.
You can't go to their house
without Foreman's permission.
Don't need it.
I'll talk to
the toxicology PhD upstairs.
What about gifts
from South America?
Anyone send any fruits
or vegetables?
I don't think so, no.
Barraco azul...
I'm gonna need
your boyfriend
to collect samples
of plants
in and around your house.
Toxins are the most...
Barraco azul...
O que e isso?
Barraco azul?
Wait,
you understand him?
What's he saying?
He's--he's repeating,
"blue shack."
You know what that is?
Is it somewhere where
pesticides may be kept?
It's where we had
our first date.
Do you have a cleaning lady
who might bring
her own supplies?
What's he saying?
If it's not relevant
to the case, I don't care.
And neither should you.
Please.
This might be the last time
I ever know what he's thinking.
When I saw her waiting...
Waiting for me
at the table...
The way her eyes looked
when she smiled...
I felt like crying.
I knew that she was
the woman I wanted to marry.
Every time I see her,
I say...
La esta ela.
There she is.
He's still in there.
Quem e ela?
What did he say?
He asked who you were.
Don't get your hopes up.
Have your boyfriend
give me those samples.
How'd you even know
to look for a tumor?
Well, Dr. House noticed hormone
levels in your blood,
and consulted me
as an oncologist.
Who cares how they found it,
okay? They found it.
Are there any side effects
to the treatment?
Some nausea, dizziness,
and as the tumor shrinks,
there will be
behavioral changes.
Like what?
Well...
The tumor interferes
with certain natural systems.
Um...
It lowers libido and causes
erectile dysfunction.
Eh...
Y-you mean
the treatment will,
um...
M-make me want
to have sex?
Wh-what if I don't
want the treatment?
I would strongly advise...
You have a brain tumor, okay?
You have to have the treatment.
Okay, look,
I know who I am, okay?
And I'm not one of them.
Hey, look, we'll adjust.
Okay?
We can go through
this together.
You mean have sex?
I can't make you do that.
Maybe it won't be so bad.
It'll be terrible.
It's actually pretty fun.
From what I remember.
But you said that...
I know.
I know. I wanted to spend
my life with you.
And I knew that meant
making certain sacrifices.
But a girl has needs.
You dropped in
the U.S. News rankings.
With respect,
Mr. Laffont,
that's only because
we temporarily shut down
our Diagnostics Department.
It's up and running again.
I'm actually concerned
it might be
because of the change
in management.
If you want my money,
I'll need
to see a five-year plan.
Am I boring you?
No, no, I just...
Those flowers
are from last week.
They should be
dead by now.
Excuse me?
Sorry. I have to go.
It's Reye's syndrome.
Patient had
a sore throat
a few weeks ago
before he was admitted.
Reye's in adults
is a reach.
Not if he took aspirin.
Aspirin in adults
is a reach.
Especially in a house
with locked medicine cabinets.
Wasn't in
the medicine cabinet.
Wife used to run
a floral company.
Still does a few
orders from home.
She uses crushed aspirin
in the water
to make the flowers
last longer.
So the husband
has a sore throat,
takes an aspirin
without her knowing,
realizes he's got a sore throat,
takes an aspirin,
realizes he's got
a sore throat...
Stop me whenever you like.
Have Chase start him
on steroids.
Already did.
Then why're you
telling me?
'Cause I wanted you
to hear it from me.
Oh...
There she is.
Here I am.
Your eye.
What happened?
It's nothing
I can't handle.
MRI confirmed
macroprolactinoma.
He's doing the treatment.
And the wife?
Come on.
You saved a man's life.
Course-corrected two peoples'
wildly screwed-up world views.
It's not bad
for a day's work.
I think they were happy.
Even if it was
based on lies.
Most happiness is.
Better to have
schtupped and lost
then never to have
schtupped at all.
We can't smoke in here.
We also can't summon
people into the clinic
based on a lie
motivated by a petty bet.
And yet it happens.
It's an imperfect world.
Well?
Disgustingly satisfying.
He said it was okay.
Is one of you Dr. House?
You've seen
Spartacus, right?
I got an order here
to deactivate and remove
his ankle monitor.
♪
Robbie?
Hi, sis.
♪ Gentle is the sun
It's been years.
I know.
I thought of you
on mom's birthday.
♪ I breathe it in my soul
Is everything okay?
Yeah, yeah. Fine.
I just...
♪ And I want
to let you know ♪
wanted to see
how you were.
I'm fine.
♪ And come down
♪ come down
♪
♪ innocent way of life
Bikes go faster
without training wheels.
♪ Easily we cry
Now get out.
I have work to do.
♪ Weaving through
the cracks ♪
♪ we are simply human
Whoops.
♪ You know we are
== sync, corrected by elderman ==