[Birds chirping]
(Cat Stevens)
♪ Morning has broken ♪
♪ like the first morning ♪
♪ blackbird has spoken ♪
♪ like the first bird ♪
Nice tie.
♪ Praise for the singing ♪
♪ praise for the morning ♪
♪ praise for them springing ♪
Are you at least gonna
call the cops this time?
No, then they might stop.
Just when they're
beginning to, uh...
Capture my eyes.
Come on, Dad.
Let Rodrigo do this.
Your arthritis
is obviously--
I can pick up
my own lawn.
You know,
if you wanted,
you could put an end
to all this.
Oh, of course.
There are other ways
to save the company.
I'm only moving it to China
because I'm craving
egg foo yung.
You know, I just
got off the phone
with some investors.
Yes, and they want
a controlling interest.
We get to stay here
with the people
who've been so loyal
to this company.
Everyone keeps their jobs.
It's been a family business
for 120 years.
There's no way
that I'm letting...
♪ Blackbird has spoken ♪
♪ like the first bird ♪
What's wrong?
♪ Praise for the singing ♪
[Echoing]
♪ praise for the morning ♪
Dad?
♪ Praise for them springing ♪
Dad.
♪ Fresh from the word ♪
♪ ♪
I need you to drive me
to a doctor.
♪ House 8x04 ♪
Risky Business
Original air date on October 31, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
This would totally suck.
Patient's visited China
a lot recently.
What about
the JBE virus?
Why don't you check
his vaccination record
before you make
another stupid...
O.M.F.G.
50% off cupcakes.
How sick is the patient?
'Cause this expires today.
Central serous retinopathy?
It's linked to
type "A" personalities.
Funduscopic exam was normal.
If you don't let me
read my email,
then I won't be able to read
the email to the entire staff.
From your ex-boss.
Thank you.
"Last month,
I had an incident
"involving another
P.P.T.H. employee.
"Though I can't speak
to the details of the case
"while my disciplinary
hearing is pending,
"I want you to know
that I have completed
"voluntary
sexual harassment training.
"And on a personal note,
"if my actions caused
anyone distress,
I sincerely apologize."
You are so fired.
What? He apologized.
What? Because he said
he apologized?
He's saying he's sorry
that someone,
namely you, overreacted--
namely, by punching him.
He grabbed my behind.
Word is it was
a celebratory slap
after you completed
your first-ever
AVM embolization.
He grabbed it,
he apologized for grabbing it,
and now he's taking classes
because he grabbed it.
The classes
make him sympathetic.
Which, in turn, makes
his unrepentant attacker...
Evil.
Which, in turn,
in turn, makes you so fired.
100 bucks says
I won't get fired.
Oh, you don't wanna bet me.
Oh, my.
You're fired.
I--the bet is--
- But I thought--
- After--
- then--
- I--oh--
if only...
The bet's that I'll
get fired after my hearing!
I'll take
that action too,
but you're already
a C-note in the hole.
You're late.
Considering
I don't work here,
arguably, I'm early.
Pearl earrings?
Knee-length dress.
That's not a very shameful
walk of shame.
I was at a job interview.
I hope it went terribly.
(Adams)
Thad Barton?
We only help
rich white guys?
I am an equal opportunity
exploiter.
I only help those
who can help myself.
I have a department
to re-fund.
[Buzzing]
Atropine poisoning.
He's moving
his company to China,
and his employees
are hanging him in effigy.
Could have moved on
to the real thing.
Pupils are normal.
Thyrotoxicosis?
Not...A terrible idea.
I'm gonna go
give him P.T.U.
and T.L.C.
I have no idea what
that second one stands for.
[Door opens]
Things don't seem
small anymore, they--
I woke up from a nap
and, uh,
everything went from
really small to really huge.
Well, then, these
giant balls of medicine
are not gonna
work anymore.
The change actually
makes things simpler.
Your occipital lobe
is acting up,
giving you a migraine.
I don't have a headache.
Not all migraines
present that way.
It's called
Alice in Wonderland syndrome.
Seriously?
I never joke.
Good news is,
it's treatable
with medication.
Bad news is...
It can make you
very, very late
for very important dates.
I sometimes joke.
Thank you, Doctor.
Well, if you really
want to thank me,
my department's
not really a department.
'Cause my boss says
he doesn't have the money.
Which provides a nice
contrast...with you.
We're trying to find
money in our budget
so we don't have to move
our operations overseas.
I get it.
Answer's no.
Shouldn't have
said anything.
I'm just glad that
the symptoms showed up
before you left for China.
'Cause I'm not sure
the doctors over there
would be so optimistic,
considering...
[Speaks Mandarin]
[Speaking Mandarin]
What are you guys
talking about?
Oh, just how different
the two cultures are.
For example, our opinions
on mental illness.
Here, it's considered a normal
and treatable condition.
[Speaking Mandarin]
Is everything okay?
Everything's fine.
I could have you checked
into a facility
that exclusively treats
mental disorders.
How does that sound?
Whatever's gonna
get him better.
Let's try the medication
first.
You're hired!
Oh, you guys are gonna love
Doctors Chase and Taub.
Keep your Nazi sentiments
quiet around the little one.
You got the money?
How?
Patient's
a smart businessman.
He's destroying
thousands of jobs.
Jobs are not
being destroyed.
They're being relocated.
The fact that you see that
as inherently bad
means you're
an irrational patriot.
To put it another way,
a patriot.
Patriotism is natural.
We've always relied
on our tribes to keep us safe.
It's helpful for society
if its members
have positive feelings
about that society.
Iranian women.
Drag Queens in Uganda.
Patriotism is nothing
but loyalty to real estate,
real estate that's been
conquered 800 times
by 800 different regimes
with 800 different cultures.
But each time,
it's just the best.
I claim this burger
in the name of
Queen Isabella of Spain.
I'll go check
on the patient.
I have Hepatitis C.
She got it from me.
Hey, how's my dad doing?
Ah, great.
His vision's back to normal,
and if he remains asymptomatic
through the night,
we'll be able to release him
in the morning.
Any chance that could
happen before 9:00?
Our stock dropped
a couple points today
with the news
that he's sick.
I would love for him
to get out of here
before the market opens.
No offense, but, uh,
I think it's terrible
your dad's closing down
all your American operations.
I don't think he's
moving the company out of greed.
He's moving it
out of grief.
My mom, she died
four months ago.
Non-Hodgkin's lymphoma,
and...
It's been hard for him--
living in their house,
driving down
the same streets.
I mean, he's constantly
reminded of her.
[Rapid beeping]
Dad?
[Overlapping chatter]
[Coughing and retching]
I need
an intubation kit in here!
What's going on?
Angiography showed
a hemorrhagic site
in the left lower lobe.
I think it could be
hyperviscosity syndrome.
Are you sure Foreman's
okay with this thing
in his office?
He's never gonna know.
He's actually in here
right now.
Blood count and protein count
are normal.
I think it could be
hyperviscosity syndrome.
Sorry, but after Park
sent out here hospital-wide
non-apology apology
this morning,
I assume that plagiarism
is the new black.
If it makes Andrews
look sympathetic...
Copying him makes you
look pathetic.
And I will pay you not to go
to anger management classes.
What about another
clotting problem?
Factor 5
Leiden deficiency.
It's possible.
Adams is the one who needs
to deal with her anger.
Myelodysplastic syndrome.
I heard about
your conversation
with the patient's daughter.
You were hostile.
Well, their company's
making a decision
I strongly disagree with.
Yet you were never
anything but courteous
to the racists and rapists
in prison.
Those guys made decisions
you supported?
Myelodysplastic syndrome.
I'm guessing it has something
to do with the funeral
you attended
yesterday morning.
I was at a job interview.
You got to work at 9:15.
Closest hospital with
an opening in your specialty
is 45 minutes away.
It's not possible.
My condolences.
I wasn't at a funeral.
That just leaves...
Everywhere
but a job interview.
Get out.
Who goes there?
Reveal yourself!
Now.
Well, we would.
But Orthopedics
is still squatting
in two thirds of my office,
which is weird,
'cause you got
a large check last night.
From a corporation
that's going through
a very public
belt-tightening.
Means this donation
was given under duress.
Patient didn't tell me
the whole story,
but he did say he'd be thrilled
if we didn't cash this.
[Check tearing]
Got a policy review meeting
in here in five minutes.
Good-bye.
What are you doing?
Holding your ass.
You really
didn't know?
- House...
- Just trying to help you out here.
I figure for sure
he'd punch me in the face,
thus proving
it's a natural response.
My God, you have
super-human discipline.
And glutes.
Get your hands off me.
Sorry.
Go.
Why...did you do that?
We have a bet.
But he's the chair of
the disciplinary committee.
Forget about the bet.
You two really need
to do your homework with me.
Treat the patient with
activated protein c.
If he has
myelodysplastic syndrome,
he'll bleed out.
And if he has Factor 5
Leiden deficiency,
he'll throw another clot.
Exactly.
It's a conclusive test.
There's no actual risk.
As long as you're
both paying attention,
and are both good enough
to work here.
I hear one of you thinks
I'm a real bastard.
I guess
that would be me.
Your boss uses blackmail,
and you question
my professional ethics?
Will you be instituting
worker safety regulations
in your new factories?
Oh, absolutely.
What about juice boxes
in the break room
for the children
you'll be hiring?
Charges of
child exploitation
against American companies
have been blown
way out of proportion.
My ten-year-old cousin
lives near Cebu City.
Works at
an American factory.
I am so sorry.
It's the best thing
for him.
It sucks, but the Filipino
factories suck worse,
and the schools would suck
if they existed.
So this is the family's
best hope.
Are you okay?
Is this supposed
to itch like this?
[Buzzing]
Itching.
Interesting.
Not interesting.
Already went away.
Doubly interesting.
Means we have
to explain the arrival
and the departure.
Oh.
That's real mature, House.
What do you mean?
This is outlandishly
childish.
I custom-built this puppy.
It's got 106 leds,
each one sending light
to your eyes,
slightly different
wavelength.
Turn that off.
Different wavelengths
are stimulating your
autonomic nervous system.
That's what's making you
feel like you're on a boat
in choppy waters.
Oh ho ho! Cool.
You think I'm not--
you think I'm not gonna
go to Foreman with this?
Oh, you will.
And...I'll deny it,
and he'll believe you.
But then these two
believe that the policy
of protecting American jobs
starts at home.
So they'll never
testify against me.
And you won't be able
to prove anything.
Now, if I punched him
in the face,
that he could prove.
I remember you saying
something about
how loyalty to real estate
was stupid.
This is about
reclaiming stolen property!
Loyalty to real estate
is stupid,
because loyalty is stupid.
First patriotism,
now loyalty.
You hate ice cream too?
French vanilla, yeah.
To willfully identify
yourself as something else
is a perversion
of self-expression.
I had a thought.
Other than the fact
that loyalty is the basis
of all meaningful relationships.
The daughter said
that her mother died
of non-Hodgkin's lymphoma.
What if she was misdiagnosed?
Dutch chocolate's
not bad.
Gotta give 'em that.
Her lymphoma could have
been caused by a virus,
HTLV-1, which
our patient contracted
through having sex
with his wife.
In other words,
loyalty gave him cancer.
I like it.
Start him on radiation.
[Buzzing]
Chang and Eng Bunker.
It's the most famous
conjoined twins in history.
2011 is the bicentennial
of their birth.
The best Halloween costumes
are always the ones
that need an explanation.
What took you so long?
I already lost
one of them.
You need help
with the lacerations?
No, I think
I got palliative.
Why don't you
take preventative?
Prevent what?
He got in a fight.
Which he started.
Which means he's both
irascible and stupid.
I told the drunk,
racist frat guy
the proper term
is "conjoined twin,"
not "Siamese."
I can't comment
on the drunk or the frat.
But Chang and Eng
were both, in fact,
born in Siam.
And they were,
in fact, twins.
If your name was Richard,
it would be okay
for me to call you a Dick.
But maybe
some of the tripe
you learn
in anger management class
might help keep this guy
out of here
the next time.
Sometimes,
it's incredibly satisfying
to wind up and punch someone
who really deserves it.
But when you think
about the consequences--
Okay, let's go.
I thought you wanted me
to help him with his anger.
No, I got
everything in need.
[Beep]
[Park on recorder] Sometimes...
- Sometimes...
[With playback]
It's incredibly satisfying
to wind up and punch
someone who deserves it.
[Beep] Wonder what the committee's
gonna make of that.
This is a waste of time.
There's no way that Robin
gave me an STD.
I know this is hard,
and I'm sorry
about your wife.
If you'd like
to talk to someone,
we do have grief counselors
at the hospital.
You sound
like my daughter.
I miss my wife,
but it's not driving
my decision-making.
You were CEO since 1988.
You decided to move your company
right after your wife died.
It stands to reason
that your emotions factored in.
My wife...
is the only thing
that keeps me here.
I visit her grave
once a week.
So your daughter
was wrong.
You just...really need
a lot of money.
You ever hear
of Kongo Gumi?
Construction company in Japan
founded in the year 578.
Family-owned and operated.
Building Buddhist temples
for 50 generations.
We--went bankrupt
five years ago.
You have any idea how
that last CEO must have felt?
Sorry, I...have to move.
[Buzzer]
[Beep beep]
[Grunts]
Your heart rate
is speeding up.
Do you feel any tightness
in your chest?
Yes, I figured
it was from the radiation.
I think you're having
a heart attack.
[Knock on door]
Come in.
Dr. Wilson...
I need your advice.
Um...I bet House $100
that I wouldn't get fired
after my
disciplinary hearing.
Ever since then,
he's been acting like
he's actually trying
to get me fired.
That's because he is actually
trying to get you fired.
Does he hate me?
Not sure that's relevant
to the equation.
So it's really over $100?
Not sure the amount
is relevant.
He's fighting for his honor.
He'll ruin my career.
- Not sure that's--
- What if I bet him $200
I will get fired.
He sees competing debts
with the same person
as a disgrace to the game.
He'll be even more
motivated to beat you.
If you were me,
what would you do?
You have to give him something
he values more than honor.
And you should
update your resume.
EKG and troponins
were equivocal.
It's not even clear
if our patient
just had a heart attack
or what it was.
Let's look at segmental
wall motion abnormalities.
Get him an echo
to confirm.
I need $200,000.
His company's lost
one third of its value
since he was admitted.
And you want to do
some insider trading?
I take it felonies
aren't a violation
of your parole?
It's not insider trading.
Just betting on myself
to solve the case.
Once we cure him,
share price goes up,
I pay you back.
No.
No, you don't say "no."
You...make a counter offer.
I'm not
loaning my boss money.
Fine.
I'll make you a counter.
$100,000.
$20,000.
I'll buy options
instead of shares.
More risk,
but more upside.
But that's as low
as I'm gonna go.
I could do $5,000.
Really? No backsies.
If...you double
your clinic hours.
Six a week.
I've seen how you
disrespect those patients.
So you want twice as many
of them disrespected?
Spend more hours with them,
you'll treat them
more humanely.
And this time,
a land war in Russia
will be a good idea.
Deal?
Here's what
I'm thinking.
You went to
a parole hearing,
where one of your old patients
was denied.
Hence the attire,
hence the tardiness.
And, most important,
hence the anger.
You think you can
restore the cosmic balance
by doing extra good here.
More annoyingly,
by having me do it
and deal!
[Buzzing]
[Buzzing stops]
Of course, you know...
this means war.
Oh, I know.
I mean, you'll escalate,
and then I'll retaliate,
and the cycle will continue
until we've both
gone too far,
at which point, I'll...
maybe get suspended
and...you'll go
back to prison.
Happy pranking.
[Buzzing]
Patient had V-tach
in the echo lab,
so we capped him, but...
coronary arteries
were clean.
If the plumbing's fine,
check the electrical.
EP study.
Nice idea.
Even has a metaphor
in it.
Not worth more
than my honor.
But delightful,
all the same.
I'm not going to lose.
My college roommate
is the editor
of the Yale Law Review.
She's writing
my opening statement.
You will be eloquent
in your loss.
This case boils down
to he said, she said.
He said, "I've been working
at this hospital for 15 years
and I'm taking
self-improvement classes."
She said, "I've been
a fellow for two months,
and I'm kind of weird."
No, he said,
"I'm a drunk idiot
"who thinks he can
grab girls' behinds
without ramifications."
Wait, he was drunk?
- In the hospital?
- I already told Foreman
he'd been drinking
that night.
Andrews was taking
sexual harassment classes,
not AA.
That means he didn't
get in trouble for drinking.
Which means that Foreman
signed off on it,
which means that he set
all the wheels in motion.
Forget that.
Wild speculation.
Go do the EP study.
You already knew Andrews
was drinking that night,
didn't you?
Yes.
I think you should
cancel my hearing.
I hope this isn't going
where I assume it's going.
You're the one
who brought Andrews in.
You set the wheels
in motion.
We had a patient
who was going to die
without
an AVM embolization.
Andrews...was the only
neurologist I could reach.
He told me had
a few glasses of wine,
and that he shouldn't do it,
but he also said
that you were good.
You were ready to do one,
as long as you were supervised.
So we agreed
that he would come in,
but wouldn't
touch the patient.
I can understand
the rationalization.
We'll see
if the Board agrees
when I tell them
the whole story at my hearing
[sighs]
I already did.
I had a closed session
hearing last week.
The Board decided to dock me
two weeks pay.
Oh.
Been working for House
for two weeks.
It's already too long.
No sign of any
electrical abnormalities
in the right atrium.
I'm so dead.
I-I think House set me up.
Have you sent
the committee
a character reference for me?
I thought you
don't like favors.
I don't like gifts.
It wouldn't be a gift.
I would just be you
telling the truth.
I hardly know you.
[Beeping]
O2 sat is 89.
Did we perforate?
Is he tamponading?
Heart rate's only 90.
Neck veins are flat.
Then why
isn't he saturated?
(House)
Seems healthy to me.
Let's release him.
My option to sell
Barton Foods at $34
is about to expire.
So they thought the patient
would be better by now.
Instead, I am
going to lose $20,000.
20?
Your five plus the five
I stole from Wilson.
Plus the ten
I got on margin.
You're gonna have to talk
to my bankruptcy attorney.
Unless...
There is a way that you
can get your money back.
Give me the full $200,000.
[Scoffs]
And extrapolating,
tomorrow you'll owe
just shy of $1 million.
It's your own fault.
You forced me to go
with the options here.
Your damn anger issues
are screwing with my finances.
Regular stock this time,
nice and safe.
I'm not angry.
I don't know if you're
trying to make me angry.
You refuse
to bet on yourself.
That means
low self-esteem.
So if I give you
$200,000,
I'll feel smart
and pretty.
Low self-esteem
can be brought on
by exposure
to one's relatives.
Nice clothes
and anger...
Classic symptoms.
Family gathering.
You were late
the other day
'cause you were
having breakfast
with grammy Adams
or cousin Itt.
And she was nagging you
about finding a husband.
All right, this
is getting annoying.
I'll just tell you
what I was--
Ah, ah, ah, ah!
No spoilers.
They ruin everything.
Pulmonology was that way.
Our patient's lung problem
is not a lung problem.
It's a brain problem.
We're consulting
with Neurology.
That's my old boss.
You don't actually think
this is neurological.
I don't know what it is.
Maybe I should just
accept the patient's death,
if getting help
can lead to awkwardness.
Dr. Andrews.
My associates.
Doctors Adams and Park.
Ah. Nice to meet you,
Dr. Adams.
Hello, Dr. Park.
You two
know each other?
It's a small world.
Dr. Park, maybe
you'll like to update
our esteemed colleague
on the condition
of our patient.
Micropsia, bleeding,
tachycardia,
and difficulty breathing.
[Crinkling candy wrapper]
Cute butt, huh?
Can we go now?
You really wanna
turn your back on this guy?
Sorry.
Carry on.
Uh...Well...
It sounds like
there could be
spinal cord involvement.
Have you considered
normal pressure hydrocephalus?
Okay, normal pressure
hydrocephalus
going once.
Normal pressure
hydrocephalus going twice...
It's not his spinal cord,
it's the wiring between
his heart and his brain.
Autonomic
dysregulation syndrome.
You do a tilt table test,
see how his heart rate
responds.
That'll confirm.
Well, if he has
normal pressure hydrocephalus,
a tilt table test
could put him in a coma.
Then it's a good thing
he has A.D.S.
Do you really
believe in this diagnosis?
Because if this is
just a pissing contest,
you are at a severe
anatomical disadvantage.
It's autonomic
dysregulation syndrome.
No...it's normal pressure
hydrocephalus.
Do a spinal fluid test
to confirm.
We're doing the tilt table.
That makes sense.
You'd rather have House
fire you than Foreman?
This bet's
got to be a test.
See if I can handle
working with him.
I need to prove I have
the confidence
to disobey him.
Do you have any
medical justification
for your diagnosis?
The symptoms fit,
and Andrews is a hack.
Do you think I'm right?
Let's go.
No...you need to go
prepare for your hearing.
[Whirring]
15 more minutes,
Mr. Barton.
A skin resurfacing laser
is missing.
And why are you
asking me about it?
Because you work for House.
What would House want
with a skin resurfacing laser?
I have no idea.
Have you seen it?
My feet feel hot.
That's completely normal.
No, but House has been
talking about
how badly he wants
to remove those prison tats.
It's a very expensive
machine,
and I'd like it back.
Please tell me
if you hear anything.
How expensive?
$200,000.
He took it.
I have no idea.
Park's hearing's
about to start.
You're covering for him.
I did the same thing
many times.
My advice to you--
figure out what line
you aren't willing
to cross for him.
Because, eventually,
he'll ask you to cross it.
[Door shuts]
How are your feet?
Mr. Barton?
Can you hear me,
[Gasps]
Oh, no.
We have convened
the disciplinary committee
to decide the appropriate
action that should be taken
against Dr. Chi Park
as a result of her actions
on October 7th of this year.
Dr. Park, do you have
an opening statement.
Dr. Foreman,
members of the committee,
thank you for giving me
this opportunity
to speak to you today, I...
Good news.
You can cancel
the hearing.
'Cause I'm
firing her myself.
She's not yours to fire.
You guys better
fire her for insubordination,
'cause she went rogue,
and my patient is now in a coma.
I'm the one
who did the test.
No, it was my idea!
Seriously, House?
At least
I'm smart enough
to know what
I don't know.
She went out of her way
to defy me!
She needs--damn it,
you should just fire her!
My apologies.
My apologies, Dr. Park.
Dr. House's comments
will, of course,
have no bearing
on this hearing.
Please continue.
I, uh...
I can't believe
you did that.
Right back at ya.
Our patient's dying.
We need theories.
It's gotta be normal
pressure hydrocephalus.
Andrews predicted the coma.
Yeah, but even a broken
doctor's right twice a day.
Patient wasn't wet,
wobbly, or wacky.
Coma had to be
a lucky guess.
If you didn't think
he was right,
then why did you want us
to collect his spinal fluid?
I didn't. I wanted you
to do a tilt table test.
You have a wonderful way
of communicating.
I knew Park wanted
to do a tilt table.
She listens to me,
I waste an hour.
If she defies me...
Then I get the test I want
and my 100 bucks.
Up high.
You're an ass.
You're angry.
Yes!
Now I'm angry.
Let's run the test for normal
pressure hydrocephalus.
No.
What else would
explain our symptoms
and make our patient go
into a coma during that test?
How 'bout
hepatic encephalopathy?
No, we already tested
his liver enzymes.
They're normal.
Or his liver's so far gone
it can't even
produce enzymes.
That's desperate.
Fits the symptoms.
And Andrews is a hack.
Go biopsy to confirm.
Unless you want
your own hearing.
You'd have
to hire me first.
(Woman on PA)
Nurse Williams to social services.
Nurse Williams to
social services.
So you do realize
that it is unacceptable
to hit someone
in the workplace?
Yes, completely
unacceptable.
I wasn't thinking.
I guess, I mean--
yes, technically,
I was thinking.
I just...It happened
so fast,
I did--I--
I...
It's like...
It's like
it wasn't even me.
I would never
do something like that.
Even though I did.
I'm sorry, I'm not
making any sense right now.
I, um...
I don't know, I...
Just really love
being a doctor so much.
And I barely even have
$100 and...
Please don't fire me.
Is this theory more promising
than the others?
We'll know
in a few hours.
How are you holding up?
Other than the fact
that my dad's in a coma...
Terrible.
Tomorrow morning,
I am supposed to sign
a piece of paper
that will...
move the company
and cost thousands
of employees their jobs.
I thought you'd
rather see the company
go under in New Jersey
than thrive in China.
It's what my dad wants.
And it's still his company.
I'm really just
keeping the seat warm.
But unless he wakes up
before tomorrow,
it's gonna be my signature
on that piece of paper.
You don't have to sign it.
I'll let you know
when we have the results.
Biopsy was clean.
It's not his liver.
I also ran
the spinal fluid test,
and you were right
that Andrews was wrong.
His ICP was not normal.
It was elevated.
What about HTLV?
We ruled that out
three days ago.
Because of his
heart problems, but--
Once something gets
taken off the board,
I'm the only one who's
allowed to put it back on.
[Imitating crowd cheering]
You owe me 106,804 won.
Or $100 U.S.
[Imitates explosion]
God, but you're petty.
Okay, so...two options.
Either we figure out
what's wrong with this guy,
or we figure out how to make
this company profitable
in New Jersey.
Eastern equine
encephalitis?
[Buzzing]
Thinking in here!
Brain scans indicate
it could be Loa loa disease.
[Buzzing continues]
Ah, shut it off!
Apparently we're allowed
to do this now.
Get out of here, House!
Start the patient
on plasmapheresis.
He'll wake up in an hour.
It's been a pleasure
having you in the neighborhood.
[Grunts softly]
This diagnosis was brought
to you by the letter "y."
Dad...
God, you're okay.
I'm thirsty.
That's a side effect
of not dying.
Turns out your blood
was getting thick and syrupy.
Complexes of large,
y-shaped antibodies
were clogging up
your blood vessels,
causing your organs
to shut down one by one.
Now, usually with
hyperviscosity syndrome,
it's caused
by an elevated blood count
or protein count.
Yours eluded us
'cause it was caused
by antibodies
from your
rheumatoid arthritis.
Now that they're
being filtered out,
the blood would be...
A little less duck sauce
and a little more soy sauce.
So I'm gonna be
completely cured.
It's not all about you.
Your stock price
will be completely cured.
Once you sign this.
It's a press release.
It says that you're healthy,
you're going back to work,
and you're
signing the lease
that officially
moves the company to China.
He just woke up.
Dad, you don't have
to deal with this right now.
Ah, mm, yeah, actually...
He does.
'Cause the market
opens at 9:00 a.m.
And this means
a lot to me.
You may remember me
from the time
I saved your life.
If you move it,
it'll be without me.
I know you object.
I know you disagree with--
Dad...
I can't do it.
If this is really
about family,
you will not do this.
[Indistinct chatter]
Morning.
Got lucky this time.
No, you didn't.
I made this bet
so you'd stop
actively trying
to fire Park
so you'd be neutral.
You went out of your way
to help her.
She obviously
earned your respect,
passed
whatever test you--
I sabotaged her hearing.
You do read
the school paper, don't you?
[Chuckles]
If you had sabotaged
her hearing,
she would have gotten more
than a slap on the wrist.
What you actually did
was make her emotional
and make the board members
see her as a victim.
'Cause the panel
feels badly
for incompetent doctors
who nearly kill people.
You know that everyone
on that panel hates you.
You know the minute
you recommend firing anyone,
they start discussing
how big a bonus to give them.
That's just hurtful.
The fact is,
winning $100 from you
gives me more pleasure
than winning $100 from her.
Here's your five grand.
What five grand?
Just take it.
Trust me.
Found her sleeping
in the park.
Said she ran away because
her daddy didn't love her.
And that is exactly
what happened...
as far as you can prove.
Congratulations.
You're not going
to jail...Today.
But you do know
I just can't let this slide.
You need to keep up
your rep.
Fine. Clinic hours.
I'll double them.
Okay.
12 hours a week.
No...
Three times two
equals six.
And 3 times 2
times 2 is 12.
I know about your deal
with Adams.
Call Chase and Taub.
Get 'em in here.
The boys are back.
This check
is for significantly more
than what I told you
it would take
to fund the department.
I know.
You paged me?
Congratulations.
You caught your boyfriend
cheating that morning.
You had a big fight.
That's why you were late.
You re-pitched an S.T.D.
You haven't gotten
two consecutive minutes
without using
the word "loyalty,"
which explains the anger
and the low self-esteem,
and the desire
to feel pretty...
After having been rejected
explains the clothes.
It wasn't my boyfriend.
It was my husband.
I was at my lawyer's office
signing the divorce papers.
Wow.
I missed the fact
that you were married.
We've been separated
for almost a year.
So...old news?
No anger left?
It's all bought
and paid for.
(Cat Stevens)
♪ Morning has broken ♪
♪ like the first morning ♪
♪ blackbird has spoken ♪
♪ like the first bird ♪
♪ praise for the singing ♪
♪ praise for the morning ♪
♪ praise for them springing ♪
♪ fresh from the word ♪
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==