Good afternoon, Cedarville!
It is my distinct honor
to present
our annual
community service award
to one of our most
outstanding citizens.
Now, many of you
may recognize him
as coach Bob of our champion
little league team.
And some of you may know him
as the treasurer
of our harvest scholarship fund.
But I know that all of you
know him as the guy
that owns the only
gas station in town.
Bob Harris, get on up here
with that beautiful family
of yours!
Bob Harris, folks!
Bob, your community activism,
charity work,
and character represent the
finest Cedarville has to offer.
Please accept this
on behalf of all of us
and know that we love you.
Are you all right?
Bob?
You're crushing me!
Wake up!
I think you're having
a heart attack.
I'm gonna call the ambulance!
No. Just drive me
to the hospital.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
As the new dean of medicine,
I'd like to personally welcome
all of our new employees
and ask, why the hell
do you want to come back?
Tired of surfing.
He hasn't changed.
And neither has the job, right?
We still get to do crazy crap?
Save people's lives
instead of just their noses?
About that...
About the crazy stuff?
Here we go.
He's gone from ally to enemy.
He has no choice.
He's the boss now.
He has to be professional.
He has to base his decisions
on what's best
for the entire hospital.
We can't take it personally.
Couldn't have said it
better myself.
You did.
I'm just reading
the notes on your desk.
He also wants us
to spy for him.
Not spy.
I'm trying to keep House
out of prison.
To do that, I need to know
what he's doing and planning.
Spy.
Come on, guys.
I am your boss.
You do have to treat me
appropriately.
But it doesn't have to be
awkward and weird.
Outside of work,
I still consider us all friends.
I'm glad you feel that way,
because I do have
a favor to ask.
I told House I couldn't come
back until next week.
He said he understood completely
and that I was fired.
So...
Since I have my kids
for the next two days,
I need a babysitter.
No!
Male patient
went into v-fib
but shows no signs
of heart disease
or any other symptoms,
for that matter.
What was he doing
when his heart decided
to do the mambo?
He said he was at work.
You're late.
According to my calendar,
I'm a week early.
Beard's a nice touch.
Lets everyone know that
you're not a teenage girl.
Oh, now, you two
make a cute couple.
And you two...
It's not important.
Dr. Park.
You're a lot taller
than I thought you'd be.
And I look forward
to working with you as well.
He's lying, not just Taub-the patient.
These abrasions
on his knees-
they're minty fresh...
About ten hours old.
He got them
playing flag football.
He said he got them
I'm sure that's true if "flag"
is a euphemism for "penis"
and "football" is a euphemism
for "entering a vagina."
Why lie about it?
Everybody lies.
Speaking of which,
how are your two baby girls?
Wow, twins-
Congratulations.
Awkward!
He knocked up two different
women at the same time...
At least he thinks he did.
You have them DNA tested yet?
Why would I?
They look just like me.
But they will grow.
Find out what else
he's lying about.
Do an exercise test-
See if you can get him
to go back into v-fib again.
But we could end up causing
another cardiac arrest.
Hopefully.
Then we'll know what set it off.
He means it's better
to do it here
where we can revive him
than have it happen
somewhere else.
The prodigal son has returned.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to go slaughter
a fatted calf for lunch.
I told you,
I was sitting at my desk
when the attack happened.
These rug burns
are from last night.
We think you were having sex,
but memory loss
could also be a symptom.
Maybe we should ask your wife.
Don't.
I- I did something
stupid last night,
but it was
a one-time thing.
You have no idea
how bad I feel about it.
Your guilt is between
you and your wife.
We just need to know
what happened.
I was having sex at a motel
when I started to feel
light-headed.
Next thing I knew,
I was laying on my back.
I could barely breathe.
Is everything all right?
We'd like to perform
an exercise test,
re-create the stress that
may have caused his symptoms.
He was sitting at his desk.
It's his heart
we're worried about.
The test will monitor
its rhythm
so we can check
for any abnormalities.
I spent a month in solitary.
You don't think
I can keep this up all day?
I have a headache.
Could you just lower your voice?
Chase and Taub are back!
You want me to pick up
an ice-cream cake?
I also think that Taub
has brought
his little Taubettes
into work with him today.
Why would he do that?
Because I didn't give him time
to do anything else.
Then I started wondering,
who'd be sappy enough
to watch them for him?
They're not here.
What?
I just came for a chat
with a friend.
What's that I smell, friend?
I understand your confusion.
I was eating a baby for lunch,
and...
I have a massive migraine.
Will you please just go away?
You should probably
lie down and rest.
Yeah.
I was trying to.
Oh!
There is one more thing.
He's in too good of shape.
We need to get him to the point
he was at last night.
Well, don't look at me.
But if you want to...
Cute.
But I didn't mean
physical stress.
Don't you guys think
this is irresponsible?
It's like you getting two women
pregnant at the same time.
I just mean the part about
the odds of it happening.
They had to be incredibly high.
And if we induce v-fib,
odds say that we'll be able
to revive him.
But there's always
a chance we can't.
It's extreme and reckless.
That's House.
You get used to it.
Or I fire you.
Look what I found...
Kiddie-winkies!
I wonder who they belong to.
Give me my kids.
No. I genuinely wonder
who they belong to.
I need a DNA sample.
I'm not letting you
DNA test my kids.
Already did.
This swab's for you.
Fine. If you don't mind paying
a fortune in child support
for some other guy's kids,
no skin cells off my cheek.
His heart rate's
finally elevating.
Dr. Chase said you had
something to tell me.
We were talking about
how you got the abrasions
on your knees-
The flag football game.
Oh, um...
Yeah, honey, I'm gonna need you
to let the guys know
I'm not gonna be able
to play on Saturday.
The whole town knows
that you're in the hospital.
I wouldn't worry about it.
That's not what
you wanted to tell her.
You said the game
wasn't typical.
Something happened
that you were upset about?
I don't understand.
What are you-
I don't f-
I don't feel very w-
What's happening?
It's not his heart.
I know.
He's having a seizure.
There wasn't any abnormal
electrical activity
in his E.K.G.
when his seizure occurred.
It wasn't caused
by a v-fib.
We still can't rule it out.
His E.K.G. from the E.R.
documented-
Myocarditis-
viral infection
weakening the wall muscles.
We need to biopsy
his heart to confirm.
Myocarditis wouldn't cause a seizure.
Could be genetic-Brugada syndrome.
Oh, my God.
Two prodigal sons.
Come on.
Let's hug it out.
You really like the idea,
or you just want to grab some hair
for a DNA test? It's a stupid idea.
We would have seen evidence
of Brugada in the E.K.G.
You know, this is...
This is just messing
with my Feng Shui here.
What about over there?
A Pheochromocytoma.
Excess adrenaline
can cause heart problems
and... seizures.
Boring!
I'm sorry.
I thought I was here
to treat the patients,
not entertain you.
Would it hurt to do both?
Oh, this is much better!
I said it was boring.
I didn't say it was wrong.
So I'm right.
Nope. You're wrong.
Photic epilepsy-
It's equally boring,
but it has the advantage
of possibly being right.
Give him an E.E.G.
to confirm.
If you ever hear me mention
anything about wanting kids,
please feel free to punch me
in the liver.
Why?
It's like Satan's alarm clock.
What's House up to?
He hasn't asked me for anything.
He's been incredibly
well-behaved.
He's doing his clinic hours.
That is a sign of concern.
And you know him
as well as I do.
He needs to constantly
establish he's the Alpha dog.
He's got his team back.
He's got his office back.
He's got everything he needs.
You really believe that-
He's content?
I don't want to let
House sabotage himself
by sabotaging me,
and I need your guidance
and your trust to do that.
No, no, no.
Cuddy had a problem with House,
she came to me.
Wanted to vent-me.
How did that turn out?
You have a problem with House,
deal with it,
or find someone else who can.
I'm sorry about earlier,
but we needed
to provoke a reaction.
It worked.
I can barely look her
in the eyes anymore.
I'd want my husband
to tell me the truth.
Sure.
You'll feel better,
and she'll feel what-
devastated, betrayed?
Heartbroken.
Do you really
want to do that to her?
No.
But I can't live like this.
But she can.
All set.
All right, we need you
to sit back and try to relax.
Just look at the light.
What exactly are they
building back there?
A dream.
The E.E.G. didn't show
any abnormal brain activity.
He doesn't have Photic epilepsy.
I know, because he has
a Pheochromocytoma.
You said I was wrong.
You were wrong not to
rule out epilepsy first.
That only takes
a couple of hours.
Finding a tumor that's flushing
adrenaline through his system
is gonna take all night.
Monitor his brain activity,
start a continuous urine test
and blood draws
every two hours.
I can't!
I have my kids!
Wilson's leaving
in, like, 15 minutes!
Chase and Adams can
do the test. Thank you.
For the massage bed.
You and Park
are checking the motel
he was bumping uglies at
for environmental factors.
He couldn't find a babysitter.
Get over it.
You're gonna get us killed.
She thinks I'm a prostitute
on her turf.
Showing weakness
is what gets you killed.
Why would she think
you're a prostitute?
I'm in a dump with a guy
almost twice my age.
What else is she gonna think?
How old do you think I am?
So who cheated on you?
We just met.
Don't you think
it's a little early
to be dragging up our baggage
in front of each other?
Who says I have baggage?
I know when House
went to prison,
you quit medicine.
- You don't do that unless...
- I didn't quit.
I took a vacation.
I knew when he got out,
I'd get my job back.
House didn't even know
he was coming back.
I had faith.
Now, that has baggage
stamped all over it.
Seizure activity?
No. One of the sensors
came loose.
I'll fix it.
What is it?
Not a Pheochromocytoma.
Our patient now has
a mass in his neck,
and his body temp's been rising
over the last three hours.
Where is the construction crew?
Well, I'm not gonna make
them work day and night.
So I chose night.
And his urine and blood tests
didn't show any evidence of
an adrenaline-secreting tumor.
Meningitis. We can do
a lumbar puncture to confirm.
Sorry. I had to drop
my kids off
at day care across town.
What'd I miss?
It's not meningitis.
His neck isn't stiff,
and his mental status is normal.
He's only guessing.
I'm talking to Taub.
He can't say "my kids"
until he lets me test them.
Tell me about the love shack
where he cheated on his bride.
Quarters came in handy.
My kids loved the massage bed.
Lab tests show the bed
tested positive for, uh,
semen, vaginal secretions,
saliva, and fecal matter,
both human and animal.
Probably want to boil the kids
for a couple hours
when you get home.
The bathroom
also tested positive
for five different types
of pathogenic bacteria.
Fusobacterium necrophorum was one of them.
Yeah. How'd you know?
The bulge in his neck.
Bacteria colonized
his parapharyngeal space,
moved into his jugular vein,
causing a thrombus-
Lemierre's syndrome.
Treat with amoxicillin
and clavulanic acid.
Take out the clot
before it moves to his lungs
and kills him.
You got at least
a trillion cells.
You're gonna misplace
one of them eventually.
I have to tell
my wife the truth.
There's plenty of time
for that after the operation.
What if I die,
and one day she finds out
I cheated on her?
I'll never be able to explain,
never tell her how sorry I am.
You're increasing
the odds of that
every second we waste here.
No, I'm not agreeing
to anything until I talk to her.
Daddy!
Hey.
Hey, guys.
Ew!
Your neck looks really gross.
I missed you both so much.
But I need to ask you favor.
I need to talk to mommy
alone for a second.
Would you mind
watching them for us?
This guy's an idiot.
I think he actually
has a good point.
What would you think
if you found out years later
your beloved dead wife
cheated on you?
I wouldn't believe it.
As long as I don't
hear it directly from her,
then I can hang on to hope
that it's not true.
But this way...
She has to either dump him
or forgive him.
Guys, get your stuff.
We're leaving.
I'm so sorry.
I'll be back.
I'm gonna drop our kids off
at my mother's.
Look, he made a mistake...
A stupid, horrible mistake.
But we'll get through this.
All I care about right now
is that my husband gets better.
Sorry about yesterday.
House was like the child catcher
from chitty chitty bang bang.
Why is he so obsessed
with my kids being my kids?
Because he sees insecurity,
and when House senses weakness,
he pounces,
and because his insecurity
is the fact that other people
can have faith
and don't have the obsessive
need for physical proof.
Also, he started a betting pool
on which kid is yours
and which isn't.
An entire hospital betting
on the legitimacy of my kids?
It's great to be back
among friends.
I'm not the bad guy here.
I'm betting on them both
being yours.
I would have donated
the money to charity.
Approaching the clot.
Stand by for...
It's not a clot.
It's his lymph nodes.
The bulge wasn't caused
by pus or blood.
It's tissue inflammation.
- How can there be that much tissue?
- Lymphoma.
We need to take a biopsy.
Did I Nick something?
I don't know.
I don't see any bleeding in here.
His sclera's jaundiced.
I think it's his liver.
It's failing.
We did a major operation
for no reason.
It's not Lemierre's syndrome.
We would have had to biopsy
his lymph nodes anyway
to check for cancer.
Which it's not.
Biopsy was clean.
We could be dealing with
an alcoholic
going through withdrawal.
It explains his heart,
seizures,
and liver failing.
But not his swollen
lymph nodes.
Why are we stealing
cable from here?
We don't even have a TV
in our office.
I'm an ex-con
trying to adjust to a world
that's passed me by.
Stealing's all I know-
That and the fact
that I was right
about what's wrong
with our patient.
Just wrong about what?
He means it's not Lemierre's,
but it's still an infection,
which is why
it's spreading so rapidly.
Cultures take time, and his
liver doesn't have much left.
That's why
we're gonna blast him
with broad-spectrum
antibiotics.
The blast will fry
what's left of his liver.
The cure will kill him.
Not if we get him
a liver transplant first
and then treat him
with a broad spectrum.
And old team for the win!
Not that I'm keeping score.
It's more of a grid
where I assign numerical values
to determine who gets raises,
vacation time,
and my respect.
We have him on the donor list
for a liver.
But these things take time.
So he could die
before he gets one.
It's a possibility.
But we have another option.
We can do
a partial liver transplant
from a living donor.
I'll do it.
If you're a match,
but to increase our odds,
we'd like to get your friends
and family tested as well.
Is it safe?
It's a major surgery.
The donor spends a week
in the hospital
and up to three months
convalescing at home.
I can't ask someone
to do that for me.
There are hundreds of people
who would do that for you.
Because they don't know
the real me.
You are a good man
who made a mistake.
Then I have to tell them first.
I have to live with this too.
I know.
And I'm sorry, but...
This is the only way
that I can do this.
Before I ask any of you
to sacrifice three months
of your life for me,
I have a confession.
I had an affair.
I cheated on Denise.
I wouldn't blame anyone
if you decide-
I forgive him.
That should be enough
for all of us.
Thank you so much
for coming here-
There's more.
Larry...
That new transmission
I put in your truck-
You didn't need it.
Joe, same thing
with the engine rebuild.
In fact, I cheated
most of you here tonight.
Half the time
you bring your cars
into my garage,
there's nothing wrong with them.
I've been ripping you all off
for years.
I also took $10,000 from
the harvest scholarship fund,
and I lost it gambling.
I'm sorry.
I'm not the man
you thought I was.
That went over well.
Out of the two donors
who didn't walk out,
both were negative
for a potential match.
Telling the truth may have
just killed this guy.
I told him to tell
his wife he cheated,
not confess every sin
he's ever committed.
If everyone did that, we'd never
find a donor for anyone again.
Everybody doesn't lie,
cheat, or steal
from their friends.
Yeah, they do.
Maybe not as much as this guy,
but if people told
nothing but the truth,
the world would probably
burn down overnight.
Some people think
it's burning now.
Maybe if everybody
didn't lie...
Aw, that is cute.
I'm talking about your breasts.
They always get perky when
you're being painfully earnest.
Truth.
It's uncomfortable, isn't it?
More truth-I only noticed
because Chase
was staring at them.
He'd never admit it, because
he doesn't want to offend you.
Same reason he'd never tell you
that he's thought
about having sex with you.
Although, to be fair,
every man you've ever met
has thought
about having sex with you.
They'll lie,
because if you knew...
You probably wouldn't want
to have sex with them.
And that's just some of the lies
from the last minute.
And here's a bigger one-
You already know this,
but you pretend you don't
because it makes you
feel civilized.
Most people find it easier
to ignore the truth.
Ask Taub.
Our patient can't wait
for a transplant
that's never gonna come.
We need to get reckless
and extreme.
C.T. his liver,
find the damaged area,
and cut it out.
Hopefully, what's left
will be enough
so we can start treatment
with broad-spectrum antibiotics.
I'm sorry the first time
I had both of you together
I had to work.
But daddy's boss is what
we call a jackass.
Good. Stay right there.
I'm also sorry...
For what I'm about to do...
Because...
Because nothing will ever change
how I feel about you guys.
But...
But daddy is weak
and needs to know.
Okay.
Just gonna put this
right here... Okay?
It's 3:30 in the morning.
Why are you still here?
House is here
and apparently prepping
for an operation
that will probably
kill a patient.
I wouldn't be doing this if
I thought there was another way.
There is.
He needs a transplant.
You have one lying around?
'Cause he'll be dead
if he doesn't get one
in the next few hours.
That falls
under natural causes.
- If you kill him, we're looking at...
- Dead is dead.
Not as far as our lawyers
are concerned.
I'm not being a dick.
This is a real issue,
and I have to worry
about the big picture now.
I don't.
I'll be doing what you
would have done a year ago.
I'll be in surgery.
Chase...
You need to check this out.
This is a C.T. scan
of his liver
from ten hours ago...
This is from now.
It's healing itself.
When I left the room,
he was telling her
about the strippers
from his bachelor party.
Liver function
has improved 30%-
Buys us a few extra days
before he'll need a transplant.
Interesting question is,
why is it regenerating?
And scene.
Now we're back
to boring reality reality.
His liver was in shock before.
He's been having an allergic
reaction since he got here.
Could explain why his symptoms
appeared so rapidly.
And maybe starting to go away.
We need to run a scratch test
to find out what set it off.
Or who. This all started
when he cheated on his wife.
He's allergic to a person?
Or something
she's wearing-
Makeup, perfume,
birth control method,
her "Hello Kitty" doll.
Two of you go find her
and find out what.
Two of you start treatment
with corticosteroids
and epinephrine
while you run the scratch test.
You think I did this to him?
Or something you wear,
own, use, or gave him.
I gave him a condom.
He didn't have one.
What kind?
I don't know what kind.
I got it from the health fair
I was working at.
You're in the medical
profession? I'm miss Cedarville.
The health fair
is one of my responsibilities.
Is another one hooking up
with 38-year-old married men?
I guess I'm supposed
to be the good cop.
I know this is tough.
But anything you can remember
might help save his life.
He was giving me
a ride home, and...
He always seemed so nice.
And then we ended up
at the motel.
And now everybody's talking
about it.
And if they find out it was me,
I'm gonna lose my title
and probably my job.
And no one in town is ever
gonna speak to me again.
I made a mistake,
and now it's gonna end up
ruining my life.
Denise never wants
to see me again.
What did you think
was gonna happen?
I was sick of living a lie.
Everybody loved me.
Everybody looked up to me.
But...
I didn't deserve it.
Everybody makes mistakes.
They just don't usually
broadcast all of them
at the same time.
Well, if I'm gonna die,
I might as well do it
with a clean soul.
And if you live?
You didn't just burn bridges.
You torched, nuked,
and salted the earth with them.
Everybody has to pay
for their sins.
Oh, it feels like
you stuck me with a hot poker.
An allergic reaction.
It's the swab for
wheat-based allergies.
I've been eating wheat
my entire life.
I'm not allergic to wheat.
Now it feels like
my whole body's on fire.
This doesn't make any sense.
He broke out with a rash
right after I tested
with the wheat-allergy swab,
but none of his blood samples
show he's allergic to it.
Then he's not allergic to it.
Could the corticosteroids
have somehow caused it?
I didn't hook them up yet.
After he broke out,
I wanted to confirm it was
gluten before we dosed him.
Could be a latex allergy.
Started with a condom,
and we kept it going
with our gloves and equipment.
He doesn't test positive
for that either.
None of his samples
test positive for anything.
Then he's allergic
to something not on the tests.
I'll keep looking here.
We'll start the steroids
and see if it clears up.
You have one patient
and three DNA results?
How else do I compare them
to other genetic disorders?
What's up?
Chase basically called me
a sellout.
Just because you hung up
your lab coat for more money
and a bigger office?
I hung it up because
someone had to run this place
after Cuddy left.
There are a lot of good
administrators out there,
not many good doctors.
More to it than you think.
For example,
you're looking at monkey DNA.
My analysis-
House took your results
after he manipulated you
into providing them.
He's shedding his skin
like a snake.
If it was an allergic reaction,
the corticosteroids
and epinephrine
would have made him better,
not worse.
Is everyone trying
to think of an answer?
Or is everyone afraid to say
what they think the answer is?
I take it you're in
the latter category.
Stevens-Johnson syndrome-
It fits all of his symptoms
and explains
why he got worse
after the steroids.
Most medication
exacerbates the condition.
There's no treatment for it.
It fits.
Case closed.
Why don't you go home
and get some sleep?
I feel like I'm in hell.
We can't give you
too much pain medication,
or we'll make
your condition worse.
I got one final
confession to make.
What's left-
You cheated on your taxes?
I'm a murderer.
I killed my business partner.
I shot him in the head.
I made it look like suicide.
And he was just the first.
You killed more?
Uh-huh.
Three...
Or four.
Try not to kill anyone else
until I get back.
It's neurological.
There's an aneurysm
in the anterior communicating
artery of his brain-
The area moderating
impulse control and compulsion.
As it grew larger,
so did the confessions.
Watch.
Bob, one of my shoes
is missing from my locker.
I'm so sorry.
I- I needed the cash,
and, um,
the locker was open.
I never heard
of a neurological problem
that causes someone's skin
to fall off.
Because there isn't one.
The aneurysm
is just another symptom.
It's not the cause.
You add them all together,
we get...
We get Kaw...Kawas...
Kawas...
It's Kawasaki's disease.
It's autoimmune.
Yes, we knew what "Kawah" meant.
We just figured since it
basically presents
only in Asian children-
Which you might have,
by the way.
Which is basically
why we missed it.
Rug burns-
Certain carpet-cleaning
chemicals
have been linked to it.
Start treatment with
intravenous immunoglobulin.
Monitor the aneurysm.
If it doesn't resolve itself,
we'll have to repair it.
The rest of you...
Aren't surfing enough.
Monkey DNA-
Nice touch.
Really?
You don't think
I should have gone with rat?
I've been second-guessing
myself all day.
Where are the DNA results?
First admit that I was right.
You manipulated me
into doing it.
Yeah, I'll admit to that.
Now you admit
that it was incredibly easy,
because you can't cheat
an honest man.
I love them.
I don't care if one of them
isn't biologically mine.
What about both?
Could be.
Haven't read these.
Now say I was right.
No. I'll admit
I was weak for a moment,
but I'm not doing this.
I don't care.
You do, and I'll prove it.
I will shred this.
I will call off my pool,
return the money,
and we'll forget all about it.
Or we'll go to the light box
in the lab
and know the truth
once and for all.
Stop.
Let me see them.
Just wanted to make sure
all three were inside.
The mayor checked.
There wasn't any money missing
from the scholarship fund.
Dr. Chase told me...
About your disease,
how it made you confess
to crimes you hadn't committed.
The affair with that girl...
Is that real?
Honey, I...
Would never...
Have never cheated on you.
I knew you could never
do that to me.
I don't know how...
But I knew.
Glad to see taking a year off
didn't dull your skill set.
I got lucky.
About the other night...
I have enough problems
with this job.
Second-guessing
my best doctors
shouldn't be one of them.
Why are you up here?
You have your own bathroom
and office now.
Shower. I haven't left
the hospital in four days.
Why?
House won't go home.
And there's no way I'm leaving
him here unsupervised.
House is screwing with you...
By not screwing with you.
He's watching TV
and drinking Martinis all night.
Meanwhile, he's keeping you here
searching for a plan
that doesn't even exist.
How the hell
did I not see that?
I'm glad you're back.
Me too.
Either a hot tub or a sauna.
A hot tub would be cool.
New team, old team...
I present...
Phase one
of operation outer office 2.0.
Nothing's changed.
Oh, everything has changed.
No.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com