And you're sure he didn't
leave until after 9:00?
Absolutely.
We watched
the Devils demolish
the Rangers.
The game started at 7:00.
Neither of you stepped out
between periods, get beer,
pick up a pizza?
- We stayed at my place.
We were together
the whole time.
And you said the Devils won?
- Yup. 4-zip.
Kovalchuk had two,
Arnott and Parise each had one,
and Marty got the shutout.
I'm sorry.
Marty?
Martin Brodeur.
Devils' starting goalie
for, like, the past 20 years.
He played awesome
as usual.
Your Honor,
may I submit the sports page
from the New Jersey Chronicle
on October 9th, 2011.
Objection.
Relevance.
Goes to the witness's
credibility.
Go quickly.
Would you please read
the caption under the photo?
[Clears throat]
"Martin Brodeur stops 1
of his 36 saves on the way
to a shutout victory."
That's what I just said.
That the defendant couldn't have
possibly committed the robbery
because he was with you
watching Martin Brodeur
shut out the Rangers.
Yes.
Thank you.
Your Honor, may I submit
the Chronicle sports page
from October 10th?
Your Honor.
This is what you call
going quickly?
Just two more questions.
I promise.
Please read the highlighted text
at the bottom of the page.
"In Sunday's sports section,
New Jersey Devils goaltender
Johan Hedberg was..."
That's it.
Keep going.
"Misidentified
as Martin Brodeur
in a photo caption
and box score."
An understandable mistake.
Given that Martin Brodeur
was scheduled to start
but bowed out
after taking a shot
to the throat in warm-up.
Which brings me
to my most relevant question.
Did you and the defendant spend
the evening of October 8th
watching the Devils game
on TV,
or did you just read
about the game in the Chronicle
while concocting
this false alibi?
[Clears throat]
Um...
I...
I, um...
Excuse me,
Your Honor,
may I approach?
You sure you don't want
to wait
till after he answers
your question?
No.
I'm gonna need
a continuance.
Now?
You're one answer away
from destroying
their whole defense.
- Come on.
- Oh, shut up.
You know it's true.
- Let's finish this up.
- I can't.
Why the hell not?
Because I think
I'm having a heart attack.
(Judge)
Great. Call an ambulance.
♪ House 8x08 ♪
Perils of Paranoia
Original air date on November 28, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
[Massive Attack's Teardrop]
♪ ♪
Thinks he had a heart attack
but didn't.
His EKG, cardiac enzymes,
and catheterization
are all normal.
'Cause it's an anxiety attack.
Probably because
he just turned 40
and still goes
by the name "Tommy".
It's not anxiety.
The E.R. Docs interviewed
his wife.
She confirmed
he's been feeling fine.
Nothing out of the ordinary
at work or at home.
Probably also believes
that he thinks
Salma Hayek's breasts
are too big.
Which is why I had them
admit him anyway
and treat with alprazolam.
No improvements.
Because...
Because for some patients
the diagnosis
of anxiety disorder
can actually increase anxiety,
which is also why I told him
he had
a minor respiratory infection
that was easily curable
by the medication.
You lied?
I ruled out heart attack
and anxiety disorder.
Interesting.
I know.
(Taub)
Impressive.
What, the wiliness
with which Foreman
ruled out anxiety
or his complete
wiliness-less-ness
before he met me?
(Taub)
The fact that you managed
to smear jelly
on nearly every page.
Shingles could cause chest pain
before a rash appeared.
Pain would be restricted
to one dermatome.
It wouldn't cross them.
Asthma-induced pneumothorax
would
and might not show up
on a posteroanterior X-ray.
No history of asthma.
They did a lateral view
as well.
No sign
of a pneumothorax
or deep sulcus sign.
I treated an inmate once
with similar symptoms
after he tried to poison
his cellmate with chlorine gas.
He didn't realize sharing a cell
also meant sharing the air?
Chlorine gas pools
near the ground
he thought he'd be safe
in the top bunk.
Well, why would anyone try
to poison our guy?
(Taub)
He makes a living
sending people to prison.
But he's not in prison,
and it's kind of hard
to gas a guy unless you can seal
him in a room first.
Which is why Arceus
created a universe
with 3 states of matter
and 300 solid
or liquid poisons
that could cause
his symptoms.
Arceus?
Look it up.
And alkalinize his urine.
Go search his home,
talk to his wife,
see if you can get her
to tell us what she used.
Wait, why would you think
his wife poisoned him?
Because dangerous people
don't break into your home,
they live in it.
And although his kids
are old enough
to want daddy dead,
they're still to young
to do anything about it.
(Taub)
Must be such a pleasure
to live in your head.
You're right.
Kids might be precocious.
You handle his house.
You handle him and his wife.
They get to just hang out
and do nothing?
If you need help,
you can take whoever you want.
- I'll take Taub.
Interesting.
No, it's not.
It was a 50/50 choice.
I'm totally fine
with Taub or Park.
Cool.
I'll take Taub.
And I'll take Park.
That was fun.
Not really.
[Elevator dings]
Nice move, boss.
Lying to the patient.
I had no choice.
I knew
House wouldn't take the case
unless I ruled out anxiety.
You need a girlfriend.
To keep me
from lying to patients?
To give you the excitement
you need
so you don't go looking
for it.
You're not working
for House anymore,
which means
you no longer have him
to blame
if you get caught.
I'm not looking
for excitement.
I'm doing my job,
part of which
is to make sure
House does his.
Girlfriend might not be
so bad.
It's less dangerous
than where you're headed.
And that's from a guy
with one alimony
and two child support payments.
(Adams) It's this new curve control
thing.
It automatically slows
the car
when it senses
I'm taking a curve too fast.
You really think
I care about your car?
Or are you just trying
to avoid talking
about why you don't like
working with me?
There's nothing to talk about.
House liked poking ant hills
with a stick
when he was a kid,
and now he wants
to do the same with us.
House is an ass,
but he's an intuitive ass.
He obviously noticed something.
Yeah, the fact
that we work well together.
He thrives on conflict and is
looking for someone to torment.
Don't let it be us.
(Olivia) I don't see
how that's possible.
Tommy's the most popular guy
in his office.
He's even had defendants
thank him
after they were sentenced.
Why would they thank him?
Because he doesn't treat them
like scum.
He makes them feel
like he's helping
by offering a plea
or even just by letting them
pay their debt
and clear their conscience.
And even if someone wanted
to poison him,
I don't see
how they would do it.
He never eats or drinks anything
that we haven't made at home.
Wait.
You mean literally?
Like, not even a bottle
of water?
No.
So he was obviously
afraid of something.
Yeah, rats,
mice, cockroaches.
(Tommy)
My first job out of law school
was at the health department.
If you'd have seen
some of the kitchens
or the processing plants
I have,
you'd cook
all your own food too.
Poison wouldn't have
to be in food.
Have you gotten
any strange letters
or packages
recently?
No.
You also wouldn't have
to be at work.
We've got two young kids.
There's definitely
no poisons
I could have accidentally
been exposed to at home.
What if it wasn't an accident?
How are things
between you and your wife?
[Laughs]
Are you asking me
if I think
my wife is trying
to kill me?
Yes, I am.
Absolutely not.
This is coming
from a man
whose eyes
are wide open.
I have prosecuted hundreds
of despicable acts
by husbands, wives,
parents.
I can assure you...
I love my husband,
and I would not ever
even for a second
consider doing anything
to hurt him.
(Adams)
No pesticides,
fertilizers,
or fuel in the garage.
You find anything?
No, there's not even a bottle
of wite-out in this place.
Maybe we should look again.
Maybe we should leave
before the police get here.
Well, even if a neighbor
saw us break in
and called 911,
unless they said we were armed,
it's low priority.
We've got another five minutes.
He's a prosecutor.
Obviously he knows
a lot of cops.
His house is not gonna be
low priority.
Good point.
Wait.
The dining room's
on the other side of that wall.
(Adams)
Yeah, so?
But it ends,
like, three feet further over.
You've got to be kidding me.
A second ago,
you wanted to run like hell,
and now you want
to look for secret passages?
There's a magnet
on the fridge
they use to open
child-proofed cabinets.
Go get it.
Hurry up.
Here.
[Tapping]
[Suction]
Holy crap.
[Cell phone ringing]
Don't tell me.
The jealous wife
in the dining room
with bipyridyl herbicide.
(Park)
We didn't find any poisons.
Well, you obviously found
something.
Yeah.
A hidden bunker with enough guns
to defend Fort Knox.
Or break into it.
Cool.
That's impossible. You must have
broken into the wrong house.
Then you have
creepy neighbors,
because there were photos
of you and your kids all over.
I don't understand.
How could this...
I had it put in
during the remodel last year.
But we went over the plans
together.
It's not in the plans.
I didn't want
the city to know about it.
I'm sorry.
I should have told you.
I just...
I didn't want you and the kids
to worry.
About what?
Tommy, what is it?
Why would you think
you needed so many guns?
You're not gonna believe this.
Imperio absenti chaos regit.
He's worried that "too big
to fail" applies to our banks
but not our government.
How'd you know?
Because that's what
every idiot with a bunker
full of assault rifles
is scared of.
Heather Sweeney.
Uh, it'll just be
a couple of minutes
till someone's ready
to see you.
Maybe it's not stupidity.
It's a symptom.
Cocaine abuse can cause paranoia
and chest pain.
This isn't necessarily
paranoia.
Societies do fall apart.
Look what happened
with London and the riots.
There's a difference
between an isolated riot
and the fall
of civilization.
April Donaldson.
Sorry.
Misspoke.
Imagine what would happen
if there was
a terrorist attack
on the food supply
or a pandemic where we had
to ration antibiotics.
- That's ridiculous.
- Ouch.
Oh, shut up.
We know what you're trying
to do, and it's not gonna work.
It was a little harsh.
Stop being so...
What? Paranoid?
You're gonna look pretty foolish
if that was the wrong guess.
I think you're a good person
and a fine doctor,
but it's ridiculous
to think anyone needs
an arsenal of assault weapons.
He's obviously paranoid.
What about Fahr's disease?
He's not hallucinating.
As far as we know.
We should do
a mental status examination
and get a CT
of his basel ganglia.
No, we shouldn't.
If it's not poison, it's most
likely atrial fibrillation
brought on by hyperthyroidism
or sleep apnea.
[Spits]
Looks like we got ourselves
a good, ol'-fashioned cat fight.
No, we don't.
We have
a reasoned disagreement.
Still there's only one way
to settle this.
Actually there's two,
but we don't have enough jell-o
for the first.
Mini-mental,
CT,
and get a hair sample
to check
for past cocaine use.
Check his TSH levels
and get a sleep study.
Sorry, we got to make it
a fair fight,
which means
you're stuck with her.
He's not "stuck" with me.
And it's not a fight.
Uh, excuse me, miss,
what is your name?
Mariel Wilkerson.
Huh.
You don't look
like a Mariel.
You're up.
So what do you think--
is the patient paranoid or am I?
I don't think
stockpiling weapons
is the most reasoned response,
but, given what I've seen
at Bloomingdale's
on Black Friday,
I wouldn't say it rises
to the level of mental illness.
And me?
Again, given what I've seen
at Bloomingdale's...
Don't let House get
to you.
It's all of you.
I feel like you don't
respect me.
Chase certainly
doesn't try to hide it.
Chase respects you.
He's just more comfortable
working with me
because he's known me longer.
And I'm not just saying that
because you own a gun.
I don't own a gun.
I've thought about it,
but I'd probably end up shooting
someone in my own family,
like when my brother
tosses his toenail clippings
behind the couch.
What about you?
If anarchy breaks out,
I plan to do
what my ancestors have done
throughout the ages--run.
(Foreman)
Sounds like a good plan.
You got a moment?
Stop telling the nurses
I'm looking for a girlfriend.
What makes you--
Two lunch offers
and a box of cupcakes
since this morning.
So a few people
are nice to you,
and your first thought is,
"Hmm, this seems strange"?
I haven't even had enough time
to eat my own lunch,
much less run around trying
to recruit nurses for yours.
So can I get back to work?
You're lying,
aren't you?
It's for his own good.
He's not paranoid.
He's just stupid.
Well, shouldn't you put yourself
in that group?
You own a gun.
Our patient doesn't own a gun.
He owns an arsenal.
And I don't own a gun.
Yes, you do.
And you're a felon,
so you'll end up back in jail--
That is actually not one
of the many reasons
that I don't own a gun.
Why would I need a gun?
The only thing I own
worth protecting
a thief would need a crane
to get out of my apartment.
You don't own anything
you need.
You own things you want.
And you're definitely the type
who'd want a gun.
You like anything dangerous--
monster trucks,
motorcycles, fireworks.
Everyone loves fireworks.
Watching them,
not making them.
I'm telling the truth.
I stand corrected.
If you believe me,
then this issue will be resolved
with no further action
necessary.
Absolutely.
It's not resolved,
is it?
Not even close.
[Door opens]
It's not cocaine.
Hair samples were clean.
It's not looking good
for Fahr's either.
I'm not seeing
any calcifications.
You sure?
They can be pretty hard
to detect
in people under 50.
- See?
- What?
We all disagree
all the time.
It's not just me
and Park.
Nice try,
but I'm not getting
in the middle.
So why didn't you want
to go with her this morning?
She's weird.
She's not weird.
She's a good doctor.
Most good doctors are weird.
Look at House.
Am I weird?
Yeah, but you're hot,
so it's easier to put up with.
You're completely normal
and a pleasure to deal with.
You're weird.
In a good way?
Maybe we should just concentrate
on the medicine.
You own any guns?
That's not medicine.
But it's related to medicine.
Kind of.
What do you think?
Yeah,
but not for protection.
Despite what the media
would have us believe,
you think we live
in a very safe world.
You just think
they're fun.
How did you know?
Working in prison,
you learned criminals
rarely target
random strangers,
and you've got more money
than you know what to do with,
so anything that seems different
and fun's worth trying.
And you?
Not here in the states.
Back home, I keep a few
for hunting 'roos.
You hunt kangaroos?
But they're so cute.
They're also delicious.
You're screwing
with me.
Totally.
There's no calcification.
Looks like we're both wrong.
You don't need to stay.
We won't have the results
until the morning.
It's okay.
I'll stay.
Go.
I'm sure your mother's ready
for a break by now, huh?
Give the kids
a kiss for me.
You think it's the end of
the world, but you wanted kids.
Oh, honey,
come on.
I don't think
the world's coming to an end.
Look...
You have a spare tire
in your car, right?
That's what those guns are.
I mean, I hope to God
I never have to use one.
But if we can wake up
and learn
that the entire bank system
has gone bankrupt overnight,
it just seems stupid
not to have a jack in the trunk.
Just in case.
And you've always--
What's that from?
I don't know.
(Park)
You don't feel that?
No.
He also spiked
a fever overnight.
It could be TB.
You want to say it.
- Say what?
- There's no sign of atelectasis
or infiltrates
on the chest X-ray.
Yeah. It's med-speak
for she's an idiot.
Systemic sclerosis can cause
lower extremity ulcers.
It would have to be
pretty far along
because the first symptom
was just a few days ago.
His paranoia started
at least a year ago.
If he's paranoid.
(House)
So it's either not sclerosis
or it's extremely aggressive
sclerosis.
We should biopsy the skin lesion
and start him on enoxaparin.
Shouldn't we wait
for the biopsy results
before we start treatment?
Now's your chance.
She's leading with her chin.
I agree with her.
No, you don't.
Which means
you're both idiots.
Get to work.
I know you don't think
I'm an idiot.
[Drawer shuts]
Does it matter?
If you're just looking
to amuse yourself
at my expense,
then no.
But if you feel the need
to manipulate me
to make me feel useful,
then yes.
I thought
we'd gotten past that.
If we hadn't gotten past that,
you wouldn't be here.
But ability
isn't always enough.
Just ask Yngwie Malmsteen.
So this is you
trying to help me?
No, this is me helping me.
And amusing myself
at your expense.
Which brings us back
to, why do you care?
I deserve respect.
I'm a good doctor.
People respect you.
They just don't like you.
(Chase)
Where's your wife?
She just needed some time.
Not a fan of guns
I take it.
It's not the guns.
It's...
I shouldn't have lied
about it.
I'm guessing
it's a little of both.
And a little of,
"Who the hell is this guy?"
I'm not a nutcase.
I just want to do
everything I can
to protect my family.
Don't worry.
I'm sure she understands.
(Ethan) At first, I thought
it might be frostbite,
but I haven't really been out
in the cold.
And yet your first thought
was frostbite?
Yeah, I guess I was just going
by how it looks.
It looks absolutely nothing
like frostbite.
You serious?
With some difficulty.
Then what is it?
A sign that you need
to take a long vacation.
At least a month.
A vacation?
Wait, is this
like a bucket list thing?
It's cancer.
It's silver.
I'm guessing
silver nitrate
mixed with petroleum jelly
that your boss
put on the petty cash
so he'd know who to have
arrested for stealing it.
Damn.
Yeah, damn.
[Pager beeps]
It's diffused into your skin,
and the only way
to get rid of it
is to get new skin.
That normally happens
every 30 days.
So I hear that La Crosse,
Wisconsin has got
the world's largest beer can.
Here's the per diem schedules.
These are supposed
to be in the computer files.
Sorry. Since Claudine left,
no one's been inputting
the numbers.
I miss Claudine.
She left
because of you.
I thought
that was Nadine.
- Her too.
- Where are you going?
You still have an hour left.
Emergency page
takes precedence.
- Can you--
- I don't know how to use the program.
Then find someone
who does.
I got to get
out of here.
Got your page.
You're an ass.
Admit it.
Let me down.
After you admit it.
You know,
I'm a little tired.
I think I'm gonna--
all right, I admit it.
Despite the fact
that I know
there's a gun in here,
I'd never find it
because you are more devious--
- Clever.
- Devious.
[Yawns]
All right, fine,
clever.
More clever and you'll always be
one step ahead of me.
[Timer beeping]
You're either preparing
to fight Pacquiao
or you're having
one heck of a bad day.
- I'm Anita.
- Eric.
Nice to meet you.
And you can tell Taub
that he's gonna get
the same treatment
as this heavy bag
if he doesn't cut this crap out.
Who's Taub?
You know, I'm sure
you're a nice person
and you have no idea
what you've gotten sucked into,
but, really,
I'm not interested.
Okay, and I'm sure
you're a nice person,
but I just moved
from Atlanta,
and it's my first time
at this gym,
so definitely don't know
who this Taub guy is,
but I already agree.
He's a jerk.
[Laughs]
Are you sure
you don't want to start over?
Take your time.
I'll be around.
[Phone dialing]
Taub, it's Foreman.
(Taub) Hey, can't talk now.
Little busy.
What's going on?
[Shouting]
Need some droperidol
in here!
I gotta go!
He was hallucinating
he was being attacked by bears.
Points again
to paranoia.
I agree.
Except for the "again".
Acute onset points
to tularemia.
Or it's been chronic, which
points to GAD autoimmunity.
Explains
the neurological impairment
as well
as the normal blood work.
Tularemia doesn't always show up
in blood work either.
(Chase)
You know what else
doesn't show up
in the blood work?
Nothing.
This could be
all psychiatric.
An untreated schizoid disorder
he's finally lost
the ability to suppress.
Schizophrenia doesn't cause
skin ulcers or fevers.
No, but digging delusions
out of your skin
with dirty fingernails
could cause both.
I don't think
he's a psych case.
Because you're paranoid
about paranoia.
Because his symptoms
point towards an infection
that spread to his brain.
I think we should treat
with high-dose, broad-spectrum--
which will kill him
if it's a GAD autoimmunity.
Treat for GAD.
Corticosteroids
and IV immunoglobulin.
I'm not paranoid.
And they don't dislike me.
They don't even really know me.
They tell you that?
I didn't ask because
you wouldn't believe the answer.
If it makes you feel better
to think that.
You're the one
everyone dislikes.
You probably don't even think
it's GAD.
You're just agreeing with her
because you think
it'll create more conflict
between us.
There's only one way
to find out.
Actually, there's two.
We're still waiting
for that jell-o delivery.
Let me know
how it goes.
Gotcha!
You poor dumb bastard.
Touche.
[Giggles]
Mm.
[Sighs]
God, this is exactly
what I needed.
Tell me
about it.
(Man)
Anita.
Oh, my God.
Who is that, your roommate?
It's just you have to go.
Wait a minute,
what's the big deal?
Please.
I'll explain later.
Just hurry up.
Please.
You have a boyfriend?
No,
he's not my boyfriend.
He's my husband.
I'm really sorry.
(Anita) Hey! I thought you weren't
getting back till tomorrow.
His fever's going
through the roof,
which means we were wrong
about GAD
and the steroids kicked
the infection into high gear.
Or it's GAD, and we started
treatment too late.
- Increase the steroid dose.
- (Park) We can't.
If it's an infection,
we'll kill him for sure.
(House) With neurological symptoms
progressing this fast,
he's dead either way.
If we increase the steroids,
then either death comes slower,
which means we were too late
with the GAD,
or death comes faster,
which means we were too stupid
with the infection.
We were already stupid
with the infection,
but it's not too late.
He's young, and he was
perfectly healthy two days ago.
He can fight this off
if we give him a chance.
Fine.
But a shotgun
is not gonna work.
We need a sniper rifle.
Start running DNA assays
for sporotrichosis,
meningococcemia,
and any other boggle-winning
words you can think of.
You just said you wanted
to increase the steroids,
and now you want to just--
- I changed my mind.
- But--
(House) Do what Park says.
[Tommy gasping]
[Rattling]
Well, you don't have a gun,
but you do have
my sunglasses,
my tennis racket--
I can't imagine why--
Had to kill a mouse.
It was really hard with
those stupid little sunglasses.
And my money clip.
Was there any money in it?
Not anymore.
Can I go to bed now?
Or do you want
to do a cavity search?
Lock up
on your way out.
This is ridiculous.
Every moment we waste
looking for a phantom infection
is time
we could be treating him.
(Park)
For the wrong diagnosis.
If it was GAD,
he'd be having seizures.
If it was infection,
there would be
some sign of it
in his blood or CNS.
- Which there isn't.
- Yet.
I'm beginning to think we should
just go with House's idea.
This was House's idea.
He said--
no, I'm talking
about the jell-o.
At least it wouldn't be
so annoying to watch.
[Door opens]
Taub, you got a minute?
You're an ass.
You know that?
What's the problem?
Some cute young nurse
baked you cookies?
No, some guy almost caught me
making out with his wife
in their living room.
And how exactly
is that my fault?
If you hadn't been
screwing with me
and put the idea
in my head...
So you don't date anyone
unless I put the idea
in your head.
You really do need
psychiatric help.
Unlike you,
I don't need drama.
I like my job,
and I'm happy
with my life.
You're so happy
with your life
you've got nothing
better to do at midnight
than to come back into work
to yell at me?
Stay out of my business.
You're blaming the wrong guy.
Good for him.
Married one's not a keeper,
but it's a start.
You're an idiot.
[Pagers beeping]
[Monitor alarm blaring]
He has stridor
but no obstruction.
He's anaphylaxing.
Get me a trach kit.
Scalpel.
It's not working.
There's no breath sounds.
It doesn't make any sense.
His trachea's blocked
below the incision point.
We need racemic epinephrine.
We tried that already.
(Taub)
We're gonna try again.
It's our only choice.
We got him breathing,
but barely.
At least we know
tracheal edema
isn't from anything
we did
because we're not doing
anything.
(Taub) Which is a good thing,
because neither GAD
nor systemic infection
would cause anaphylaxis
or tracheal edema.
And an allergic reaction
wouldn't get worse three days
after he was admitted.
So we've got nothing.
Unless he was
still being poisoned.
(Adams)
By who?
His wife wasn't even here
when he hallucinated.
Good question.
Now we're the ones
being paranoid.
What about
squamous cell carcinoma?
If it's only in his epithelium,
it wouldn't show up
in his chest X-ray.
It is possible, but...
Wouldn't cause hallucinations.
It could if you also have
paraneoplastic syndrome.
Get a biopsy.
You think it's cancer?
I think
you should get a biopsy.
Admit it.
Two hours ago,
I found this in your closet
in a box
with your name on it.
I knew you'd move it
somewhere outside your apartment
until you were certain
I'd given up looking.
So I had to convince you
that I'd given up looking.
That's not a gun.
[Laughs]
Yes, it's a paperweight
with a handy storage compartment
for .45-caliber bullets.
- And that's not a bullet.
- Admit it.
I'm more clever
and more devious.
You can even have it back.
It's not my problem
if you go back to prison.
My problem is you thinking
you're always one step
ahead of me.
This proves nothing
because it's not a gun.
It's a prop.
From Dorothy Dietrich's
magic act.
Look it up.
She's the only woman to ever do
the "catch a bullet" trick.
I won this
off her prop master
in a poker game.
House--
it's fake.
It's plugged.
Look for yourself.
Hey, hey, don't point
that thing at me.
It's not dangerous
because it's not a gun.
House, House,
just stop it.
Fine.
What the hell
are you doing?
Pull the trigger.
Don't be insane.
They're blanks.
You pull the trigger,
I drool a little fake blood,
and then I spit out the bullet
that the audience thinks
I caught in my teeth.
Go ahead.
Shoot me.
I'm not shooting you.
All right.
I'll shoot you.
Don't.
House, don't.
Even if they are blanks,
people'll freak.
It's not real.
Which means you didn't prove
that I have a gun.
Which means
you proved nothing.
Admit it.
- All right.
- All right, what?
You win.
And it feels good.
Grr.
[Clink]
You were wrong.
Don't feel too bad.
We all were.
His trachea wasn't swollen.
It was blocked
by a pseudomembrane
growing across it.
It means he's not paranoid,
is an idiot,
and was poisoned.
What are you doing?
Give me a machida scope.
Hold his legs.
He's not gonna like this.
Because you're not gonna be able
to breathe.
But I need to see
down your barrel.
The good news is the poison
didn't come from your wife.
It came from a little bastard
of a bacterium
whose crap
can cause chest pain,
respiratory distress,
skin ulcers,
the growth of pseudomembrane
across the airway,
and, in very rare cases,
hallucinations.
Call the CDC.
Tell them we need antitoxin
as soon as possible.
Diphtheria?
(House)
We didn't guess it
because nobody gets it.
Instead of building bunkers,
you should be getting boosters.
As in routine vaccines against
stuff that is actually scary.
(Woman on P.A.)
Dr. Wills to recovery.
Diphtheria.
House pulled it
out of nowhere.
Cool.
You just getting in?
Had a meeting about a new
parking validation system.
Cool.
How are you feeling?
Not great.
[Door slides open]
But better.
The antitoxin is working.
He'll be able to go home
in a few days.
That's good news.
But we've moved out.
Oh, come on, honey.
I'm sorry
I lied, but--
I know, okay.
It was for our own good,
but I don't care.
I don't want to be lied to,
and I can't live like that.
I can't live
in that home.
Oh, please don't.
I love you.
I love you too.
Which is why you're
not gonna live there either.
I don't care
if we might need them.
I just know
that I can't live my life
feeling like we do.
It's not worth living
in fear.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
[Schuyler Fisk's Waking Life]
♪ ♪
♪ There's an anchor ♪
♪ that's pulling
on my heart ♪
♪ ♪
♪ and it's deep
in the water ♪
- Hey.
- [Softly] Hi.
Thanks.
♪ Can't take me down ♪
You know,
there's a bunch of us
going to happy hour
after work.
♪ Tracin' faces ♪
I'm craving nachos.
You interested?
Thanks, but I got
a lot of work
I need to get done.
Sure.
Well, if you change your mind,
we'll be at Rudy's.
Okay.
♪ 'Cause I'm not lost ♪
♪ just looking for the prince ♪
♪ I'm taking it ♪
♪ one step at a time ♪
- Hey. -Hey.
- Hey.
♪ I'm getting by ♪
♪ by the way ♪
♪ it's you on my mind ♪
Would you like to get a drink
sometime after work?
You mean all of us
or just us?
I was thinking
just the two of us.
Did Taub put you
up to this?
No, it was just something
I'd been thinking about
and I figured,
what the heck?
Might as well ask.
Yeah, well, it's probably
not a good idea,
you know,
with us working together.
Didn't you marry someone
you used to work with?
Yeah.
But...
All right.
Sure.
When?
Tonight?
Sure.
♪ All this time
I've been blind ♪
♪ to this waking life ♪
♪ now I see it everywhere ♪
♪ 'cause I'm not lost ♪
♪ just looking
for the prince ♪
♪ yeah ♪
♪ and I'm taking it ♪
♪ one day at a time ♪
Hey.
Changed my mind.
Okay.
♪ ♪
♪ you're still on my mind ♪
♪ you're still
on my mind ♪
♪ I can't see you ♪
♪ but I know you're here ♪
♪ I know you're here ♪
♪ I know
you're here ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I'm not lost ♪
♪ just looking
for the prince ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I'm taking it ♪
♪ one step at a time ♪
(Anita) I'm glad you changed
your mind.
♪ By the way ♪
Hey.
♪ I'm not lost ♪
♪ I'm just looking
for the prince ♪
♪ and I'm taking it ♪
♪ one step at a time ♪
♪ and I'm getting by ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==