Previously on Batwoman...
Alice was right.
Your mom's still alive, right?
If you wanna know her name...
It's not worth it.
So, what's next, Batwoman?
We find
that case of Batman's trophies
before anyone else does.
Why did you call me here?
Over a dozen weapons
of mass destruction
are belly up
in the Gotham River somewhere.
So together, you two are gonna find
and stop every freak
who gets his hands
on one of these weapons
until each of the items on that list
are found and accounted for.
Come on.
- It's not fun?
- Thank you.
Nice.
Could you be a little louder?
I don't think they heard you
in Star City.
How cold do you think
the pool water is?
You tell me.
- It's actually really warm.
- Good.
Seriously?
Okay. I get it.
You can hold your breath
for a really long time.
But I got news for you.
The world already has an Aquaman.
He's a lot more ripped.
Derek?
If you're waiting for me to say
this isn't funny, then fine.
This isn't funny.
You can come up now.
By the order of the Mayor's office
in exchange for your cooperation
in these cases
you will be remanded
into supervised custody.
If you harm
or attempt to harm any person
this release will be rescinded.
If you violate any of the laws
of Gotham City
this release will be rescinded.
If you attempt to escape,
this release will be rescinded
and you will spend
the remainder of your life
at Arkham in solitary confinement.
Any questions?
Yes.
Does this kind of wreck my ensemble?
Any questions I'm likely to answer?
I got one.
What makes you think
any of this is gonna stick?
You.
Because you're responsible
for everything she does.
She crosses the line, your days
as a caped vigilante are over.
I might even arrange for you two
to have adjoining cells.
You're tying my fate to a psychopath?
Well, more like handcuffing it,
but yes.
Until you two have tracked down
every last one of those toxic toys
from Batman's trophy case
'cause it looks like
another one's already
racking up a body count.
In a crime as cold-blooded
as the creature some say
is responsible,
two Gotham University students
are missing
and presumed dead
after blood and not much else
was found at the scene
save for a grisly calling card
which eerily resembles that
of Batman foe Killer Croc
who terrorized Gotham
nearly two decades ago
in a violent reign of
reptilian terror.
And while some insist
this may just be the work
of an attention-seeking copycat
authorities can't say for sure
whether Gotham has
a new lizard problem
or if this killer is just a crock.
And while initial searches for...
Killer Croc, aka Waylon Jones.
Former professional wrestler
who suffered from
an unidentified infection
that caused his skin to grow scales,
hence the appearance of a crocodile.
Now, as the infection progressed,
other physical abnormalities
followed.
Elongated jaw, claws, tail.
I remember him.
Batman killed him, right?
Oh, no.
No. No, Bruce tried to save him.
He took pity on him.
He always thought
that his violent tendencies
were a result of the infection.
He actually had Waynetech labs
working on a cure for his condition.
A way to reverse it, but...
They never found it though.
So, what happened?
The GCPD happened.
They had their own ideas
of how to deal with KC
so they dropped
a truckload of thermite
into the sewer junction.
Right on top of him.
Lit the primer cord and ran.
So that tooth?
Pretty much all that was left of him.
And now it's loose.
Okay, but how could a tooth
have created a whole another Croc?
I mean, I get a lizard
can grow back a whole new tail
but please tell me that tooth
didn't grow back
a whole new Killer Croc.
If the original Killer Croc
suffered from an infection
then it would've gotten
into his bloodstream.
So maybe the tooth
carried the infection.
And whoever found it...
We need to find them.
But the question is, how?
I have a question.
Why is there a tree in here?
I mean, I get the whole bat motif
but this is a 44-storey building.
Surely there's a more
comfortable workspace available.
I need to talk to you both.
In private.
I'm just gonna hang out here.
Okay. If new Croc's anything
like the old one
I'm gonna need Batwing on my six.
Where are you with figuring out
what's wrong with the suit?
Still working on it
but making progress.
Okay, well, why don't you two
put your nerd brains together
and try to fast-track a fix?
Yeah. Yeah, we'll get on it.
Knock knock.
Got my hands on a copy
of the forensics report
from the pool attack.
Fair warning, the word "secretion"
comes up in several places.
Because apparently his drool
contains a paralytic agent
which renders his victims unconscious
allowing him to feed on them
at his leisure.
I should probably
put it out there right now
that I really do not do reptiles.
Okay. Let's get Alice on this.
If crazy stuff's going down,
may as well get the crazy lady's
take on it.
We don't really use
the C-word anymore.
Crazy?
What the hell?
It seems we have a guest.
Security cleared a landing request
for the CEO of Jeturian Industries...
Jada Jet.
She's apparently insisting on
a meeting with the Wayne CEO
and will not leave until she has one.
Good luck with that.
Well, we can't exactly tell her
"Yeah, we don't know
where our billionaire CEO is."
I have a feeling she'll settle
for the acting CEO.
- Great.
- Who's the acting CEO?
Me.
Kate wanted to make sure
we could handle any problems
that arose in her absence.
Thought I'd be just a name
on a letterhead.
Okay, well, if Jada Jet
wants to meet Wayne's top-op
I may need to look the part.
Actually, you are in luck.
Because I just picked up
a ton of dry cleaning.
And why don't you try to find out
what our uninvited guest wants?
Okay.
Hey.
I know you said
you didn't want to know this
but before you sit down with her,
you should probably know that...
that uninvited guest
is your birth mother.
Okay, tell the truth.
Does this say,
"No, I haven't been CEO
for just five minutes?"
No. It says, "I'm a confident,
put together, young black woman
who you were an idiot
to ever give up."
You think she knows?
Pretty big coincidence
if she doesn't.
Then what does she want?
What do you want?
I just wanna get through this meeting
and never see her again.
And I wanna get her damn helicopter
off my roof.
Okay, what is the absolute minimum
I need to know
to get through this unscathed?
What would Bruce Wayne insist
on knowing about her?
Probably her bra size.
Wiki version,
Jeturian Industries specializes
in micro technology.
Jada Jet took control after the death
of her husband a decade ago.
Doubled the company's wealth
in half that time.
She's a fighter.
But so are you.
Send her in.
Hey, just remember,
she never gave you anything
so she can't take anything away.
You got this.
If I had known Wayne had a new CEO,
I would have sent a gift basket.
Then we couldn't meet in person.
Ryan. And it's acting CEO.
So Bruce Wayne checks his stock price
from a super yacht in Belize
while you do all the real work?
Jada Jet.
Nice to meet you.
Were you and Bruce acquainted?
We exchanged a few heated words
years ago,
when he poached
one of my most valued employees.
If your employee allowed himself
to be poached
he must've felt undervalued.
But I'm assuming
you didn't fly 12 blocks
from your corporate headquarters
to open up old wounds.
No.
I'm here to address a new one.
There was an illegal breach
of the Jeturian Industries servers.
It was a very sophisticated hack.
But the culprit left behind
a few digital bread crumbs
and we followed them back
to an IP address
belonging to Wayne Enterprises.
That's why you're here?
Well, it depends.
Is there anything else
I should know about?
Because I think corporate espionage
is more than enough reason
to have a little chat.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Ignorance of what's going on
in your company
doesn't pass for business acumen.
If you had proof, you'd be talking
to the SEC, not me.
Why are you here?
Because I didn't forge my company
into a multinational conglomerate
to have someone swoop in
and steal my life's work.
And because I believe warnings
are best delivered directly.
And I'll only give one.
Stay out of my business.
That won't be a problem.
And I think you should drop
the "acting" from your job title.
Denying you knew anything
about this...
was not your best performance.
Your dad programmed your suit's AI
to speak with his voice?
Dad, say hello to Mary.
Hello, Mary.
Give it a try.
Mr. Fox? Hi.
What was Luke like as a kid?
Calling up photo records
for Lucas Fox, age six.
Dad, belay that request, please.
It's like you can talk to him again.
That's...
That's amazing.
Well, it would be more amazing
if the suit didn't turn off
at the worst possible times.
Any guesses why?
According to this diagnostic,
the suit's failsafe got tripped
causing it to shut down.
What tripped it?
Well, the suit
tracks all kinds of medical data.
Biometrics, eye movement
electromagnetic impulses
to the brain, heart rate.
It's just constantly
monitoring the health status
of the person wearing it.
If I'm reading this right,
the suit thought you were injured.
Yeah, which prompted
a system-wide shutdown
putting the suit in safe mode.
Turning off in the middle of a fight
because it thinks
you need medical assistance
seems more like un-safe mode.
Yeah, well, there's a reason
that this thing
was under a tarp in my dad's lab
and not out on patrol in Gotham.
Still has some glitches to work out.
Well, why don't we start
by making sure there aren't
any glitches with you first?
If the suit thinks you're injured,
let's make sure you're not.
Yes.
So, let's get this monster.
Oh, I thought she found you.
Did I spy with my little eye
Jada Jet's chopper on the roof?
So you knew her name
this entire time?
She's, kind of,
like a helicopter parent,
just without the "parent."
I mean, really, what kind of mother
abandons their daughter
to the horrors
of the foster care system
to literally "Jet"-set
around the globe?
No, no.
We're not doing this.
Renee said I have to watch you.
It doesn't mean
I have to listen to you.
So you don't want to know
where Croc is going to strike next?
Fine.
Well, as the resident expert
on predatory behavior
I had some thoughts on how Mr...
chooses his prey.
I was thinking back to my first kill.
For which, I chose a geriatric harpy
with an oxygen tank.
Now, do you know why I did that?
- Because you're a killer, Alice.
- No.
Well, yes.
But that's not the takeaway.
I chose her
because she was easy pickings.
See, when a fledgling predator
is learning how to stalk its prey
it seeks
to separate one from the herd.
So he wouldn't have gone
after two victims for his first hunt.
Look at you learning
to think like a killer.
Which means the pool
wasn't this Croc's first attack.
And if it wasn't for all the blood
in the deep-end...
They would have just been listed
as missing persons.
Just like the missing persons I found
that were last seen
at the East River shore.
I'm here,
two miles from the pool of attack.
Welcome to his hunting grounds.
And with the team trailing by one
an incredible cross-field pass
from Megan Rapinoe
to rookie sensation
Whitney Hutchinson,
who fakes out the last defender
and she's on a breakaway...
and scores!
The crowd goes wild.
We're all tied-up
with minutes left in the game...
Which the refs are calling
on account of darkness.
Mom!
Arguing with the ref
will get you a yellow card.
Fine.
Gross.
According to the 911 call,
you're right in the area
where the missing girl's mother
said she was playing,
GCPD's en route.
Well, they'll find
about as much as we have.
Which isn't much.
There has to be
some sign of her there.
Drag marks
lead off in that direction.
But there's no body parts, no blood.
He didn't feed on her here.
Which is understandable
given he did just feast
on all-you-can-eat coeds.
There's a whole lot of secretions,
Sophie.
Didn't you say O.G. Killer Croc's
saliva contained a paralytic agent?
That's how he's subdued his victims.
And then stash them away for later.
It's basically like a croc-pantry
for when he wants a doggy-bag.
Okay, then we need to find
where he stashed her
because that girl
could still be alive.
Yeah.
Until he gets hungry.
Is that Croc's skin?
It appears our Croc is a growing boy.
So, what was she like? Mommy.
She was amazing.
And then you took her from me.
I meant birth-mommy.
Well, if it'll break the ice,
I'll tell you about my mom.
She had a really great head
on her shoulders.
Emphasis on the word "had."
Why do you care?
Why do you keep pretending not to?
Surely you grew up wondering
what she was like.
And seeing that fate,
otherwise known as me
has brought you together
I think I, at least, deserve to know
that my efforts have paid off.
You wanna know what Jada was like?
She was amazing.
She was confident, direct,
fearless, unapologetic.
She was a frigging masterclass
in taking what's hers.
And letting it go, apparently.
Did it hurt all the more knowing
she didn't want you in her life?
No. Because I don't want her in mine.
She doesn't even know who I am.
But I know who she is
and don't need her.
Now shut up
and help me find the trail.
Actually, I think
we just found where it ends.
You first.
Me?
The one who's not wearing
impenetrable tactical armor?
That's who you want taking point?
I'm not letting you out of my sight,
Alice.
Do you really think I'm gonna run?
Do you really think
I'm going to believe
that you give a damn
about stopping this croc?
Yeah. I think you're gonna run
the first chance you get.
So it's my job
not to give you any chances.
Oh, that's funny. I thought it was
your job was to save a little girl.
Don't act like you're here
to do the good deed, Alice.
You only think about yourself
so don't you dare use
that little girl as camouflage.
I was that little girl.
Don't act like you're the only one
with abandonment issues.
I will not give up on this girl
the way everyone gave up on me.
That smell.
Rotting meat.
Kind of takes me back
to my childhood.
What the hell is this?
Bait.
This means we're not the only one
hunting this monster.
He's not a monster.
He's my son.
This feels a bit unnecessary.
I'm fine.
Well, you're keeping fit
in my official professional
medical opinion.
Let's take a look at your heart rate.
Looks good.
Let's have a listen to your lungs.
Good breath sounds.
Your heartrate is rising.
Rising.
Still rising.
Now, it's racing.
Luke, are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah. I...
I'm just... I'm ticklish,
and your hands are cold.
Yeah. Yeah.
You're right. I...
You're totally fine.
Totally. You're totally feeling fine.
Just...
You can put your shirt back on.
Yeah. Okay.
If you want.
- You should.
- Okay.
Yeah. So like I said,
it's just a problem with the suit.
Yeah. Must be.
You think you can fix it?
Yeah. Yeah. It should be easy.
I just need to override the failsafe.
Are you sure that that's a good idea?
I mean, isn't the point of a failsafe
to keep you safe when the suit fails?
What if it's just
trying to protect you?
I think it's being
a little overprotective.
It kind of reminds me of a certain
newly-minted doctor that I know.
My boy didn't mean
to hurt those people.
I'm sure he didn't.
He's not a killer.
Unlike that one.
No.
Wasn't expecting to find anybody
down here.
Much less a pair of celebrities.
What the hell are you two
doing together anyway?
Aren't you all supposed
to be enemies?
Long story.
She's working with me.
They're little short staffed
at City Hall, that's why.
We wanna help your son.
Why don't you start by telling us
what happened to him?
It's probably better if I show you.
Just before Steven
was heading off to college
we went on a father-son fishing trip.
He hooked the bluegill
on his very first cast.
But when we cut that thing open
there was something
mighty weird inside.
Let me guess.
Rather large crocodile tooth?
Yeah.
Steven thought it would be cool
to make it into a necklace
but he cut himself on the tooth.
Cut got infected.
Then Steven started changing.
Tried doctors.
None of them knew what it was.
They couldn't stop the changes.
Every day, there was a little less
Steven and a little more...
creature.
That's when the appetite
took hold of him.
And I had to chain him up.
But he was just too strong.
Too hungry.
He broke free.
I've been trying to lure him back.
Well, you rolled up the red carpet
for him.
I can't imagine
what you're going through
but we really do wanna help your son.
And we have to start by making sure
he doesn't hurt that little girl
or anyone else.
Yeah, but I just don't think he's
gonna agree to being locked up again.
That's where this comes in.
You think that thing
is strong enough for him?
Yeah.
But it's not for him.
It's for you.
I'm not gonna let you hurt my boy.
Batwoman.
I'm reading a huge power spike.
Is everything okay?
Batwoman, do you read me?
Batwoman!
I'm sorry. I really am.
But my boy's suffered enough
without you adding to it.
I just...
I just want to get him
the help he needs.
Yeah. Your idea of helping Stevie
is taking him away from me.
Locking him in a cage, or worse.
Jab him with needles.
Dissect him like
he's some kind of lab animal.
I'm his father.
I'm gonna do whatever I need to do
to keep him safe.
Even if that means...
Stevie, no. It's your dad.
Stevie, no!
Daddy issues.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- I just need a minute.
- Oh, that's good.
Because that's all I need.
Suckers.
One minute I had her,
and then everything went dead.
I've been trying to raise her
but I can't even...
Batcave come in.
Batwoman, we read you.
What happened?
Exactly what I said would happen.
Alice escaped.
And I can't hunt her down
and save a little girl.
Batwing?
You ready to get back in the field?
Yeah, I'm good to go.
So you and Mary fixed what was
wrong with the suit?
Yes. Batwing is all clear.
Good.
Alice was last headed north
through the sewer tunnels.
If she's on foot,
she's gonna want to change that.
There's a truck depot
a few miles on that trajectory.
That's where I'd head.
I hope you're right.
Because we need to find Alice
before Renee knows she's gone.
Help! Somebody!
Help me, please.
Oh, thank God.
I thought that thing was
gonna come back.
And he probably will
when you said he'd come.
Got them. We gotta skedaddle.
I can't walk.
You're gonna have to try.
But my leg is broken.
See, I'm on a really tight
schedule here,
so you and me trying to
three-legged race it out of here
is really gonna slow me down.
But you have to help me.
Fine.
I'm gonna help you...
by teaching you the lesson
that I had to learn the hard way.
No one is gonna save you
except yourself.
You are the only one
you can count on.
And the sooner you've learn that,
the better off you'll be.
You're gonna thank me for this
one day.
No! No, don't leave me.
Don't leave me please, please!
I know you're out there, Steven.
And I know you can hear me.
There are still some of you left
in there that can understand me.
Okay, I do not want to hurt you.
I just want to help you.
And your father,
he just wants to help you, too.
He really loves you.
And trust me, you are really lucky
to have a parent like that,
someone that would do anything
to protect you.
Never give up on you.
No matter what.
So much for trying to
reason with you.
Montoya, we got a problem.
Just lost the signal
from Alice's tracking monitor.
Define "lost."
One moment it's reading
loud and clear
the next, nothing.
It doesn't make sense.
No one's ever managed
to circumvent one of those things.
And I tell that to Alice.
This means she could be anywhere.
Oh, great.
The sidekick.
It's Batwing.
Cool name.
Now let's see
if you can live up to it.
How's the suit, Luke? Any problems?
Just this distracting voice
in my ear.
Did you really think
you could beat me?
Why would I need to beat you?
We're on the same team.
Whether we like it or not.
- Was something supposed to happen?
- It already has.
Right now a thousand nanobots
are swimming through
your bloodstream.
Sending out tracking beacons
to satellites as we speak.
So if you wanna run,
you better be really fast.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
I got you.
I thought I lost you.
Congratulations.
I see you've stopped the Croc,
secured the tooth
reunited a missing girl
with her mother
but what I don't see is your partner.
She's over there.
Waiting for you to chauffeur her
back to Arkham.
Had some technical difficulties
with that
but I think we've found
a better solution.
Right, Alice?
Leaping lizards, Gotham?
You can add "bat" to the list
of apex predators,
because Batwoman
just took a bite out of Croc 2.0.
The rampaging reptile
has been relocated
to the not-so-natural habitat
of Arkham Asylum,
where I'm assuming
the guards' hazard pay just went up.
Thanks to the Caped Crusader
the Croc was denied his last meal
and missing girl Whitney Hutchinson
was reunited with her mother
in a reunion that had even the likes
of yours truly a little weepy.
And rest assured, Gotham,
these were not crocodile tears.
You know, if you squint
you can just make out Jeturian
Industries from here.
I liked it better
when I didn't know she was there.
I'm sorry.
I should never have told you.
It's not your fault.
It's nobody's fault.
Except hers.
You know, what I can't get over?
She paid a doctor two million dollars
to falsify records so no one
would ever know I was hers.
What kind of mom does that?
You don't know what her life
was like then
or what she was going through,
or even what her options were.
But there is one person
who could give you those answers.
I don't know if I want to know them.
Ryan, I know what it's like
to need to put up a wall.
Believe me,
I've laid a few bricks in my life.
But I also know
what it's like to be a girl
who just wants a hug from her mom.
What if she doesn't want me
as her daughter?
Then it'll be her loss
not yours.
Sorry, I banged up
the suit a little bit.
Dad?
Why isn't he talking?
I don't know.
Maybe it's because
you removed the failsafe.
And I think
you need to turn it back on.
I managed to pinpoint where
the suit still thinks you're injured
and it's the exact same place
where you were shot.
Yeah, but that injury's healed.
I know.
And thanks to the desert rose,
you don't even have a scar.
- Right.
- A physical one, anyway.
I think what the suit's interpreting
as physical pain
is actually psychological pain.
Mary, come on.
That's absurd.
Is it?
I mean, you've been through so much.
Just because your body's healed,
doesn't mean you have.
This is a problem.
Botanist in the lab doesn't think
this vine is one of Poison Ivy's.
Only way to be 100% sure
is to run tests on it,
but the only way to do that...
Is to open it.
But he wasn't willing to do that.
How do you know
it wasn't the real thing?
Because I've seen it up close.
And if the real thing
is still out there, then...
God help us.
Wait, excuse me, miss.
I'm afraid
you can't just go in there.
I'm sorry, Ms. Jet.
She just walked her in.
It's all right.
I dropped in on Ms. Wilder
unannounced yesterday.
She's just returning the favor.
I thought you and I agreed
you'd stay out of my business.
I am.
This is personal.
Because I'm your daughter.