Last season on Batwoman...
- New look!
- New Batwoman.
- What is this place?
- It was where Bruce
kept the weapons he confiscated
from all the villains
he took down.
When I was a kid,
I drew pictures of how I imagined
a black Batman would look.
Turns out my dad was secretly
turning those pictures
into reality.
Your mother didn't die
in childbirth, Ry-Ry.
Mommy dearest
is still very much alive.
So, what's next, Batwoman?
We're gonna find
that case of Batman's trophies
before anyone else does.
It didn't take long
for the psychiatric unit
at Gotham University Hospital
to make their recommendation
to the courts.
Wonderland Gang leader Alice
aka the missing
and presumed dead Beth Kane
will not stand trial but instead
will continue her residency
at Arkham Asylum
for the Criminally Insane.
Curiouser and curiouser.
I will show them exactly
how wrong they are about you.
And I will have so much fun
doing it.
Just as you would want,
my dear, sweet Alice.
Where were we?
Oh, yeah, side-kick names.
Just FYI,
no sidekick actually likes
to be referred to as a sidekick.
- Copy that, my number two dude.
- Nope. Not that either.
"All the more reason
for me to find a way
to get you out of there.
I promise you, I'm not giving up
on you this time.
More to come.
Your father."
Kane.
Visitor.
So I have an idea for a name.
Just please don't say
Black Batman.
Seriously, Black Batman?
Coming from the girl
who inherited her code name.
You know what, I got one.
The Dork Knight.
Just look for
the damn poison ivy.
Yeah, you sure
they shipped it here?
Believe it or not
poison ivy doesn't get
a lot of action on the dark web.
So I got creative, honed in on
people who could actually benefit
from a mystical,
fast-growing vine
and found these guys
looking for a way
to expand their marijuana crop.
Shipment was supposed
to come in today.
Of all the artifacts that fell
into the river
a poison ivy sprig doesn't
exactly scream money maker.
Bingo.
Is it just me or has this
quadrupled since Circe took it?
Someone probably just got it wet.
Keep it away from the light.
Hey. You copy?
What the hell was that?
So, what, we're sisters now?
Far from it.
I graduate med school tomorrow.
And Dad's one wish
was for me to check on you
and keep you from going off
the deep-end.
So this is me, pretending to care
so I don't have to lie to him
when he calls me tomorrow
to congratulate me.
That is so sweet.
But I'm good.
I can smell you
through this partition
so I beg to differ.
See that's the thing.
None of these matters.
Because Daddy's going to find
a way to get me out of here.
Really? From the top bunk
of his cell in Metropolis?
Even incarcerated
Daddy's one of the most
connected men in Gotham City.
What makes you believe that?
Oh, he didn't tell you.
Yeah, we've been writing.
So I know you came to make sure
that I was miserable,
but I'm sorry to inform you,
I'm not.
Fine.
Then this is me punching in
and promptly punching out.
See you, Alice.
One quick question
while I have you.
It's about your little pal Ryan.
Four down.
How many still out there?
A lot.
But at least in the meantime
we prevented Gotham
from a cortisone shortage.
So you wanna tell me
why you froze up back there?
I didn't freeze up. The suit did.
It just glitches out sometimes.
Because I can't be watching
both of our asses.
Yeah, I know that.
And I'll fix it.
Graduation tickets!
I go on at 7, which means your
butt needs to be in your seat
at 6:30, sharp.
So if there's
a bomber threatening
to take out half the city
just remember that I only become
an official MD once
and people bomb Gotham
every other day.
Now if you'll excuse me
I have to go shower off
my encounter with Alice.
Apparently, she and my dad
are pen pals now.
That's uncomfortable.
I've barely even heard from him
since he was put away
but sure,
reconnect with the chick
who killed your second wife.
I'll just be graduating tomorrow
you know, valedictorian,
top of my class
but as long as Alice knows
that you're thinking of her...
Hey, hey, hey.
I know your family
can't be there tomorrow.
But this family can.
And we won't miss it.
Oh, that reminds me
Alice told me to ask you
about your birth mom.
She was like,
"Ryan will know what I mean."
And then she smiled
like a total creep.
Your mom died in childbirth.
That's dark even for Alice.
So you don't know
what she's referring to?
Since when does Alice
ever make sense?
I can relate to Alice
on a deeply personal level
which is why I'm here
at her last known hideout
where society shoved her
back into the sewers.
At the tender age of 13,
she was lost
forgotten, held captive,
tortured.
Who wouldn't break
under all that?
Locking her away in Arkham
is just victimizing her
all over again.
You know you drank too much
when you're seeing leprechauns.
Free Alice? That woman
is a full-blown lunatic.
Alice is a survivor.
Pay her some respect.
Alice is just another victim
of a flawed bureaucratic system.
She deserves her day in court.
Dude, why did...
Why did you just say that?
No idea why I just said that.
What the hell was that?
What's happening
with your hat, huh?
Let go of me.
Curiouser and curiouser.
What the hell is going on?
Let's just get out of here, dude.
Stand still.
- Why can't I move?
- Kill him.
I'm not killing my friend, freak.
Dude, what are you doing?
No, no, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Oh, my. What the hell is that?
What did you make me do?
You psycho!
You're a freaking psycho!
Mad as a hatter.
Yo! Hey, I got something for you.
I'm sleeping, go away.
I think you're gonna
wanna see this.
Isn't that the Batman guy?
The Mad Hatter? I remember him
from when I was a kid.
Move!
I swear I would
never kill anybody.
It was like one second
I'm laughing at some loser
in dress-up
and the next thing I know I'm
slicing open my buddy's throat.
It was completely
out of my control.
What makes you think
it was the Mad Hatter?
Oh, Montoya, last I checked
you traded that big shiny pin
for a basement desk
in the City Hall.
What's it again, The Freak Squad?
Rogues Unit.
- Was he short, old, what?
- No, younger.
Lanky. Dork-like.
He's a Mad Hatter imposter.
Which means he found the hat.
No, no, what are you doing?
No, no, no!
Oh, my... What the hell
did you just do?
I don't know
what's more disturbing
that, that he posted it
or that Alice
actually has a fanboy.
Sorry, how does a top hat
make someone kill
their drinking buddy?
Right.
Meet Jervis Tetch,
aka, the original Mad Hatter.
Now, according to my dad
Jervis Tetch was a tiny, insecure
and annoying neuroscientist.
He felt like the world
wasn't listening to him
so he developed
mind-control technology
to force them to listen.
He built it directly
into his hat.
Okay, this says Bruce
had the hat deprogrammed
before he put it
in the trophy case.
My guess is that
the technology latches
to the brain activity of the
first person who puts it on.
But if the hat is technology,
can't we hack it or whatever?
It's not exactly uploaded
to the Cloud.
We, first, need to get the hat
off his head.
Well, how, without falling victim
to it in the process?
One hundred and twenty-eight
hertz of frequency.
Your dad figured out how to
disrupt the hat's radio waves.
Okay, so we know the how
and the what.
We just need to know the where.
So if I were an Alice-obsessed
Mad Hatter wannabe
where would I go?
I was wondering when
you'd come crawling back.
You stormed out of here
in such a huff last time
I was worried it was something
I said.
Tell me what you're planning
with your Mad Hatter superfan.
I told you, I don't know him.
Well, he certainly knows
a lot about you.
Have you watched the news?
My identity's been outed.
And some people
actually appreciate
that I'm just a girl standing
in front of a psychiatric ward
asking them not to fry her brain.
Oh, come on.
We both know I'm utterly helpless
behind these walls.
You came because you want
all the dirty deets on mommy D.
I saw my birth mother's
death certificate.
Nia A. Wilder.
Died the day I was born.
If you say so, dear.
What is this?
Are you lonely?
You need to keep somebody
on a leash
to stop you from slipping
into total isolation?
Am I lonely?
Look at your life.
Your closest emotional connection
is an ex in witness protection.
You have no one.
I gave you someone to fill the
hole in your little empty heart.
- I have my friends.
- Luke and Mary?
Right. Who you're so close to
you can't even tell
your birth mother lied to you
all these years.
We're done here.
Sounds like your Mad Hatter's
planning a tea party.
Do you know what he's planning,
Alice?
- I just know what I would do.
- Which is?
It would be so refreshing
if a supervillain actually said
what they meant for once.
What tea party?
Not to kill the mood,
but the last tea party Alice had
she poisoned your mom.
So what, he's making it personal?
More public?
You know what?
I should ask my dad
maybe he's chatted about it with
Alice in their correspondence.
Okay.
You, my dear, are graduating
top of your class
looking fine as hell,
might I add.
And we are standing here
talking about Alice.
Can we not let that bitch
ruin the best thing
we have going on right now,
please?
Fine. Subject change.
Who's this Deja girl
you ditched me for last night?
- I thought her name was Riley.
- Oh, no, Riley was last week.
Excuse me, I am allowed
to date multiple women at once.
So I take it you and Kate
are not happening?
Oh, no, they're good.
They're friends.
But it's too complicated
for anything more right now.
Thank you, Mary.
Yes, all of that.
Ryan Wilder,
I think this is the most interest
you've ever shown
in my love life.
At least somebody's getting
some around here.
You know, the more I think
about this tea party thing
if there's one person who can
predict a lunatic's next move,
it's another certifiable lunatic.
That's what I can't shake.
She has no reason
to make this up.
She has every reason. Because
this is all a game to her.
She's trying to feel relevant
because she doesn't
matter anymore.
Now seriously drop it
before y'all both kill my buzz.
You all know this wasn't
a cheap ass bottle of champagne.
- I'm gonna go check on her.
- I should go practice my speech.
Wanna tell me what happened
at Arkham?
Nothing.
Because Alice
was unhelpful and petulant
and everything
one would expect Alice to be.
Then if she was everything
you expected,
how'd she get under your skin?
Ryan, what happened?
She said my biological mother,
who died giving birth to me
was actually still alive,
and that she covered it all up
with a fake name
so I'd never find her.
Damn.
And as much as I don't believe
a word Alice says...
There's still a part of you
that can't help but wonder
is my mom still alive?
I take it Mary and Luke
don't know.
I don't know if I want to know.
I was told my whole life that my
dad was out of the picture
and my mom died in the hospital.
What if I have a family out there?
Want me to look into it,
on the DL?
Thank you.
Testing one, two, three.
Hey, you're not supposed
to be up here.
I got a guy matching
the top hat looney from the news.
I'm just testing the microphone
making sure
that my voice projects
all the way to the back.
Perfect, you're all here.
Gather around, friends.
It's a lovely afternoon...
for tea.
Gotham City Vital Records.
Hi, I was hoping you could
e-mail me a birth certificate.
Mail only. Four to six weeks.
Okay. Thanks anyway.
I will just hack into your system
and find it myself.
Let's see.
Who was the attending physician?
Doctor Quadaracci.
Shady doctor. Here we go.
Mayor Hartley.
See this sandwich, Montoya?
I haven't eaten since 9:30.
The Mad Hatter's a copycat.
I think he somehow gotten ahold
of the original hat
which doesn't make sense,
because Batman took it off
the streets
and locked it down 20 years ago.
Am I special or did you torture
Mayor Akins, too?
He hired me, ma'am.
To run the Rogues Unit.
I convinced him
that it's only a matter of time
before Batman's enemies
come crawling out of the sewer
looking for their toys.
And here we are.
And it's not just
the Mad Hatter's hat.
Of course, it's not.
Apparently
a cutting of poison ivy
was bouncing around the dark web
for the past three days.
If someone's leaking these back
onto the streets,
I need to see
what else is out there.
Look, I am 30 days
into this whole Mayor gig
and I'm not putting the words
"Rogues" or "Toys"
onto my budget.
What about the words
"mass casualty" and "preventable"
on your resignation letter?
Mayor, I love this city
in my bones.
And I need you to hear me
before this becomes Jim Gordon's
Gotham all over again.
It's a two drink limit,
so sip slowly.
Okay, what?
Alice was right.
- Nia A. Wilder doesn't exist.
- I saw her death certificate.
The doctor who signed
her death certificate
also signed
your birth certificate.
Two months later,
he lost his license
for an unrelated wire fraud,
so I honed in on him.
He had 25 patients in the days
surrounding your birth.
I looked into all of them.
And one came into the hospital
a day before you were born.
According to her medical file
she was suffering from a cyst
on her ovary.
So I followed the money.
She paid him two million dollars
after her "so-called"
emergency surgery.
Two million dollars to cover up
her pregnancy with me.
- Why?
- I have no idea.
But your mom's still alive, Ryan.
My dad?
Nothing. Just her.
Here. If you want to know
her name.
And if you don't, I get that too.
Two drink limit?
What are we talking about?
Let's find our seats.
Ready for your big speech?
Dr. Hall. Sorry,
I was just having a moment.
I'm sure your family
would be proud. They better be.
You're one of the best students
that's ever come
through this school.
Thank you, Dr. Hall.
Dr. Hamilton. You are the
spitting image of your mother.
"Do no harm."
Today we take
the Hippocratic Oath.
But shouldn't it be called
the Hypocrite Oath...
I mean,
doctors are supposed to uphold
the highest ethical
medical standards, right?
Instead it's "How many patients
can I see in a day? "
And, "Sorry,
we don't take that insurance,"
and "That bandage costs $300."
What happened
to the Gotham medical community?
- Did she change her speech?
- This is not her speech.
And don't even get me started
on mental health care.
Do you know the process
of institutionalizing someone?
It took our alma mater Gotham U
under the oversight
of our chair Dr. Hall
a measly 10 minutes to decide
that Alice would be
an Arkham lifer.
So what, we just give up on her?
This is not Mary talking.
He got to her. He's here.
What about the fact that she was
victimized for over a decade?
That her own family
gave up on her?
That she was replaced...
by me?
This is what Alice meant.
This is his tea party.
If you have earbuds, put them on.
I'm texting you
a disrupter frequency
to block his mind-control.
Everybody,
shut up and take your seats
until I instruct you otherwise.
The show is about to begin.
Now, if you are going to wield
the power of a god,
prove you're worthy.
Remove this man's organs
one at a time until he dies.
- You need help.
- You sound like all my doctors.
- Okay, we need to take him out.
- No, no, we can't do that.
He's already brain-jacked
everyone here.
We need to get him to reverse it
before Mary kills that guy.
How? Ask nicely?
There is one person
he'll listen to.
- No.
- Ryan
Mary is about to de-organ
the chair of her university.
- Absolutely not.
- Okay, what am I missing?
We can get Liam
to undo the mind-control.
But we have to break Alice
out of Arkham first.
It may have taken him 15 years
and several dead wives
but Daddy finally understands
that I'm still his little girl.
And he's going to use every
last resource that he has left
to get me out of this hellhole
and as far away from Gotham
as possible.
Alice, we've been over this.
Your father
is incarcerated himself.
No one is coming to rescue you.
- Oh, okay, everyone, stay calm.
- Daddy?
- What? No.
- Alice, we're going. Let's go.
- Get off of me!
- I need you to come with me!
Help! Help! Help! Help me!
I see she's found the appendix.
Starting with the
unnecessary organs first
prolonging the inevitable.
Appendix is out.
Luke, where are you?
Headed to the roof as we speak.
I can't stop any of Liam's
previous commands
only he can do that
but this should protect everyone
from any of his future commands.
Get ready to rock.
What are you doing?
Put your phones away.
Stop! Stop!
Alice, I need you.
Mary needs you.
Open!
My dad's going to take me away
from Gotham! From all of you!
- Leave me alone!
- Your dad's not coming, Alice.
He is! He told me. He promised.
In his postcards. He promised.
What? These?
This is an add from a magazine,
Alice. It's for soap.
This is a page
from the Arkham directory.
A napkin from the cafeteria.
- This is a coloring book page.
- What?
- Your dad is not writing to you.
- He sent me these.
I read them with my own eyes.
Your mind is
playing tricks on you.
Look, I get it.
You lost Ocean, your dad, Kate.
Now you're back in here,
it's too much.
He's coming.
Because he promised me. He's coming!
It's garbage! Alice!
Help us.
If you help us
you can run.
And I won't stop you.
I'm sure that was a lot.
You wanna talk about it?
There's no point.
Did you just say something?
Alice?
Alice, did you say something?
Well, I can't exactly meet my
future boyfriend in this, can I?
Mary.
I'm here. What do we do?
How do we save him?
We can't.
I took his appendix,
his gallbladder
a kidney, his spleen.
I'm down to vitals.
I have to keep removing
his organs until he dies.
- Then kill him.
- What?
Kill him. He's got no chance
if you remove anything else.
We shock his heart. He goes
into cardiac arrest and dies
just like the Mad Hatter guy
wanted.
- It'll break his mind-control.
- And then what?
Then we pray like hell you can
bring Dr. Hall back to life.
Graduates wearing
those pretentious stethoscopes.
Make them useful.
Tie them around your throats.
- What the hell happened?
- The damn suit fritzed out again.
Okay. No pulse. He's dead.
How do you feel?
Like I have my brain back.
It worked. It broke his control.
Good. Hopefully this does, too.
Charge.
Clear.
Such wasted potential.
The old strangle yourself
to death gag. It's classic.
You're supposed to be in Arkham.
Well, I had to meet
my number one fan.
What did I miss?
Do you remember when you forced
Catherine Hamilton
to reveal
what a garbage human she is
in front of all her peers?
I just did the same thing
to her daughter.
Clever boy.
It's true. Doctors are all the same.
They think they're gods amongst men.
Why should I be institutionalized?
Because you think I'm crazy?
Because I see the world
a little differently than you?
Sorry for being my own person.
I heard you filmed yourself
throwing a kitten off a rooftop.
- You heard about that?
- Yeah.
Did you see it?
Five thousand seventy views.
Tell all these people to stop.
Alice...
They have too much power.
Think about it, all they have to do
is sign a piece of paper
and surprise, you're bankrupt.
Surprise, you're addicted
to medication.
Surprise, you're labeled crazy.
Forever. And ever.
I am not crazy, Alice.
If any of these people die,
they will have a reason
to lock you away forever.
Do you think I'm crazy?
The truth.
No.
I don't think you're crazy.
If it wasn't for you,
guys like me wouldn't have heroes.
Stop killing yourselves.
Get out of here.
There.
Did that earn me a hug?
Yeah.
Frequency jammers.
You are as crazy as they come, dear.
Word of advice,
don't ever meet your heroes.
Oh, you really are the monster
they say you are.
That's me.
What the hell are you?
I didn't kill him. He is fine.
You didn't think I was actually
going to let you go.
You two-faced bitch.
I saved all those people.
- For you.
- No, for you.
Because in that warped mind,
you somehow thought today
would undo the hundreds
of horrific things you've done.
Please, this is about payback.
Because you can't handle the truth.
Don't hate me because your family
might be more screwed up than mine.
Get her out of here!
In conclusion, my fellow graduates
I challenge each and every one of you
to wake up every morning
and ask yourself,
"How can I end this day better
than how it started?"
With one more saved life,
one more cancer-free scan,
one more smile.
Because if we can do that every day
together we can leave this world
a better place than how we found it.
A happy ending to the worst
commencement ceremony in history.
Thanks. Look, today was awful
and Liam is obviously sick
but he did make some good points
about the medical community.
Like for one,
maybe we should stop referring
to troubled people
as crazy lunatics.
- Even Alice?
- Yeah. Even Alice.
Then I get to say something.
Toast time.
Mary, you have probably saved
more people than anyone in this city.
You are the person
that I go to for advice
for a shoulder to cry on
for, let's face it, pain meds.
You didn't need an MD
for the people who love you
to know that you are a true hero.
And it's really dope
we get to call you Dr. Hamilton.
Congrats, roomie.
We are so proud of you.
- We love you, Mary.
- Cheers.
Okay, not to bail early
but I need to figure out
why my suit is crashing
or Ryan will never let me be
her wingman again, so...
Wait a minute.
Wingman.
Bat wing. Batwing.
Oh, that's good.
I'll take that under consideration.
Good night.
Actually, can I show you something
downstairs?
Yeah, sure.
Okay, okay, cool. I'll just be...
I'll keep the champagne cold.
Mary, Luke, the Bat.
That's my family.
I finally have everything I want.
Why risk losing it
just to get to know a woman
who had no desire to know me?
My opinion?
Because she's still your mom.
My whole life I wanted a family.
I wanted answers.
I wanted to belong to someone
and for someone to belong to me.
But that look on Liam's face today
when Alice wasn't
who he needed her to be
it's not worth it.
I'm good.
Then consider it out of your life.
Dubai loved it.
Have the lawyers write up a contract
and get them a prototype
they can play with.
Ma'am.
Tell me you're not bringing me drama
before I've had my red wine.
Just got word of a security breach.
Then have the cyber team
do their thing,
why are you bothering me with this?
Because I don't think you want
the cyber team looking into it.
Somebody's been fishing
for very specific data.
Not on the company. On you, ma'am.
Lucas Fox.
If you're hearing this message,
it means you found the suit.
Dad?
Dad, how am I hearing your voice
right now?
Because I'm your dad.
And I always know when you need me.
I have never seen you before.
You a cop?
Fortunately for you, no.
How do you have this list?
Over a dozen weapons
of mass destruction
are belly up
in the Gotham River somewhere
and your main concern is how I know?
I'm cleaning it up.
I'm sure that warms
the parents of the kid
whose buddy slit open his throat
the other night.
- Where'd you get this list?
- From me.
In exchange for my freedom.
I don't know who you are,
but teaming up with Gotham's
most prolific criminal
is going to blow up in your face.
It worked out well for you today.
You and Alice stopped a madman.
And he's just the beginning.
Why did you call me here?
You're strong and you have access.
She's got the mind of a psychopath.
So together, you two are gonna find
and stop every freak
who gets his hands
on one of these weapons
until each of the items on that list
are found and accounted for.
Hard pass.
It's just as easy for me to shut down
your illegal vigilante operation...
Ryan Wilder.
Well...
all that time my boyfriend,
father, sister
spent trying to break through
to my good side...
Silly them. It's so much more fun
on my bad side.
So do we have a deal or what?
Oh, yes, I for one am in. Yeah.
Batwoman? Answer the question.
You in
or you hanging up the cape?
Sounds like I don't have a choice.