- AAH!
- OHH!
AAH!
HELP! AAH!
OHH! AAH!
UGH!
PAM!
PAM?
OHH! OHH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I THOUGHT THE WATER
WOULD REVIVE ME.
I WAS WRONG.
I NEED TO GET MY STRENGTH BACK.
OH!
HOW'D YOU DO IT, MAMA?
3 JOBS, VOLUNTEERING AT CHURCH,
RAISING ME.
YOU WERE LITERALLY
EVERYTHING TO EVERYONE,
AND YOU DIDN'T BREAK A SWEAT.
I JUST...
I CAN'T GET OUT OF MY DAMN HEAD.
WHAT AM I DOING WRONG?
PRETTY SURE IN THE REAL WORLD
THIS WOULD BE AN HR VIOLATION
OF APPROPRIATE
WORKPLACE BEHAVIOR.
GOOD THING IT'S NOT
THE REAL WORLD.
YEAH. WELL, HURRY UP
BECAUSE YOU'RE BREATHING
LIKE DARTH VADER
AND MAKING ME FEEL BAD
ABOUT THAT BAGEL
I HAD FOR BREAKFAST.
GREAT. THEN YOU CAN HELP.
- YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT?
- NOPE.
DOES RYAN KNOW?
NOPE.
DOES THIS HAVE SOMETHING
TO DO WITH MARQUIS JET?
NEVER THOUGHT
I WOULD SEE THE JADA JET
LOOK SO DEFEATED.
WHEN I GOT YOUR MESSAGE,
IT SOUNDED LIKE YOU'D BEEN PUT
THROUGH A WRINGER OR TWO.
JOHN DIGGLE...
IT'S GOOD TO SEE
YOU, OLD FRIEND.
SO...
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME
HOW AN OLD FRIEND CAN HELP?
SUNLIGHT'S NOT WORKING.
IT'S BEEN 10 YEARS, PAM.
GIVE YOURSELF SOME TIME.
TIME? I'VE HAD NOTHING BUT TIME.
NO. SOMETHING'S WRONG.
MY ENERGY'S DEPLETING
SO QUICKLY.
DIDN'T STOP YOU FROM ATTACKING
TWO INNOCENT FISHERMEN.
THE LAKE'S CATCH AND RELEASE.
THEY WERE CREATING AN IMBALANCE
IN AN ALREADY
VULNERABLE SPECIES.
OH. 10 YEARS, AND SUDDENLY,
IT'S LIKE YESTERDAY.
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING
WOULD HAPPEN
WHEN YOU FREED ME?
I WASN'T.
I GOT WRAPPED UP IN THE MOMENT,
SEEING YOU, THE WHITE TULIP,
THE MEMORIES, THE GUILT.
AH. I'M SO SORRY THAT YOU
HAD TO FEEL GUILT, RENEE,
WHILE I ROTTED FOR A DECADE
WITH NO WATER, NO SUNLIGHT,
NO SOUL MATE.
MUST HAVE BEEN
REALLY AWFUL FOR YOU.
I AM SORRY, PAM.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO BELIEVE THAT?
I NEEDED YOU...
MORE THAN ANYTHING,
AND YOU'RE THE ONE
THAT PUT ME THERE.
I KNOW HOW TO GET
YOUR STRENGTH BACK.
I COME BEARING SUSTENANCE.
VERY MATURE.
I WAS ABLE TO KEEP JADA
OFF OUR BACKS
WHILE WE HUNT PAM ISLEY.
"DEAD FISHERMAN AT LOEB LAKE"?
FOUND WITH WEEDS
TANGLED AROUND HIS LEGS.
SO THIS IS HAPPENING?
YOU'RE GONNA GIVE ME
THE SILENT TREATMENT
FOR THE REST OF OUR LIVES?
UH, A LITTLE BUSY, SOPH.
UH, YOUR GIRLFRIEND RENEE
IS ON THE LOOSE
WITH AN ECOTERRORIST.
SHE'S NOT MY GIRLFRIEND.
OK. UH, SO CAN WE ASSUME
THAT THE DEAD FISHERMAN
IS THE O.G. IVY AND NOT MARY
CONSIDERING, HE'S,
YOU KNOW, DEAD?
THERE WAS ALSO
AN UNNATURAL HORNET ATTACK
REPORTED AT A PESTICIDE
FACTORY LAST NIGHT.
INJURED 6 EMPLOYEES.
MATCHES WHAT I FOUND.
A NEARBY DRILLING
OPERATION GOT SHUT DOWN
BECAUSE OF A TIPPED OIL RIG.
OK. ALL THESE ATTACKS
ARE ENVIRONMENT-BASED.
THAT'S PAM ISLEY'S M.O.
I'LL TRIANGULATE THESE SITES.
EVEN IF WE DO FIND HER,
THEN WHAT?
I'VE ACTUALLY BEEN
WORKING ON THAT.
SO THE DARTS ARE FILLED WITH A
PARALYTIC DRUG AND A HERBICIDE.
SO IT WON'T KILL HER.
IT'LL JUST SLOW DOWN
HER SYSTEM LONG ENOUGH
FOR US TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO
RE-CREATE THE DESICCATION SERUM.
GOOD NEWS, BAD NEWS.
ALL OF THESE ATTACKS ARE
WITHIN A TWO-MILE RADIUS
OF A GENERAL LOCATION.
SUPPOSED TO START
WITH THE BAD NEWS.
BAD NEWS IS...
THIS IS THE LOCATION.
THE NATIONAL PARK?
WE'RE GONNA BE HUNTING
MOTHER NATURE
IN THE MIDDLE OF MOTHER NATURE?
I'M DOWN IF YOU ARE.
HEH. EVER WATCH A HORROR MOVIE?
WHEN BLACK PEOPLE GO
INTO THE WOODS,
THEY USUALLY DON'T COME OUT.
BLACK PEOPLE NEVER
WRITE THOSE MOVIES.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE
FLIP THE SCRIPT?
I HAD NO IDEA THINGS
HAD GOTTEN THIS BAD.
WHEN MARQUIS WAKES UP,
THERE'S NO DOUBT HE'LL
GO AFTER HIS SISTER.
THAT'S WHY I CALLED YOU.
I WANT TO OFFER YOU
A JOB AS HEAD
OF MY SECURITY DETAIL.
YOU'D BE PROTECTING
RYAN, ME, THE COMPANY
LIKE OLD TIMES EXCEPT
FRANKLIN'S NOT IN CHARGE.
I AM.
WELL, THEN IT'S EXACTLY
LIKE OLD TIMES.
I KNOW THERE'S A WAY
TO FIX MY BOY.
CALL IT HUBRIS OR NAIVETEÉ
OR A MOTHER'S WILL,
BUT I WILL NOT
LOCK HIM UP IN AN ARKHAM CELL
FOR SOMETHING THAT
WASN'T HIS FAULT.
JADA, I APPRECIATE
YOU THINKING OF ME.
THANK YOU, BUT I CAN'T ACCEPT.
WHEN YOU OFFERED TO COME BY
IN PERSON, I GOT MY HOPES UP.
WELL, I JUST SO HAPPENED TO
BE IN GOTHAM ON OTHER MATTERS.
YOU EVER THOUGHT ABOUT
HELPING YOUR SON'S PSYCHOSIS
BY GOING BACK TO THE SOURCE?
THE JOKER'S JOY BUZZER?
THAT'S WHAT I'M TRYING TO DO.
EVERY NEUROLOGIST
I'VE TALKED TO SAYS
THAT ANOTHER JOLT WOULD
REAWAKEN HIS EMPATHY,
BUT I HAVE SPENT MILLIONS
LOOKING FOR THE BUZZER,
BUT NO ONE'S SEEN IT SINCE THE
JOKER DISAPPEARED YEARS AGO.
- IT'S GONE.
- MAYBE IT'S NOT.
BEEN FOLLOWING YOUR NEWS.
THE MAD HATTER,
KILLER CROC, MR. FREEZE,
ALL BATMAN'S ENEMIES,
AND NOW THEIR WEAPONS
JUST SHOW UP OUT OF NOWHERE?
DO YOU THINK THEY'RE
PART OF SOME COLLECTION?
I THINK THEY WERE, YEAH,
AND SOMEHOW, THEY MADE
THEIR WAY ONTO THE STREET.
AND CONSIDERING THE JOKER WAS
BATMAN'S GREATEST ENEMY,
MAYBE THE BUZZER'S
OUT THERE NOW, TOO.
I HAD SOME FOLKS OVER AT A.R.G.U.S.
LOOK INTO THIS.
A FORMER POLICE OFFICER,
A RENEE MONTOYA,
NOW WORKS FOR THE MAYOR'S
OFF-BOOKS ROGUES UNIT,
LOOKING INTO ALL
OF THESE EVENTS.
MAYBE IT'S WORTH
THE TWO OF US POPPING BY
TO SAY HELLO.
I READ ABOUT THIS PHENOMENON
WHERE PLANTS COMMUNICATE
THROUGH ACOUSTICS IN THE GROUND.
WIND BLOWS
AT A CERTAIN FREQUENCY,
FUNGI SEND DISTRESS SIGNALS.
IT'S CALLED NATURAL NETWORKING.
THAT'S KIND OF HOT.
YOU... READING GLASSES ON,
HEAD IN A BOOK,
THINKING ABOUT FUNGI.
I FIGURED THE CUTTING
BATMAN SAVED
INFECTED MARY HAMILTON
FOR A REASON.
HMM. MY SPORELING.
YOUR WHAT?
A PIECE OF ME CREATED HER
TO BRING ME BACK TO HEALTH
LIKE A BATTERY WITHOUT A PLUG.
IF I CAN DRAW HER HERE,
SHE'LL REVIVE ME.
WELL... LET'S HOPE
THIS WORKS THEN.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
ONE TRIPLE-SHOT FRAPPE,
EXTRA SWEET CREAM
AND CONVENIENTLY
FREE OF CHARGE. HEE!
OH, AND I HAVE A GIFT FOR YOU.
HOW ABOUT AN ALL-INCLUSIVE
VACATION TO SANTORINI?
WHY SANTORINI?
UH, CUTE BIKINIS,
NONSTOP SUNSHINE,
FAR, FAR AWAY FROM GOTHAM.
NEED I GO ON?
TCH! NOPE.
AHH. BUT I'M IN CHARGE
OF THE MUSIC.
I REFUSE TO LISTEN
TO A BOY BAND SING
ABOUT CONDIMENTS FOR TWO HOURS.
BRAIN FREEZE.
AGH. NOT A BRAIN FREEZE.
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
LOOK. I ADMIT I ROYALLY
SCREWED UP WITH RENEE...
SLEEPING WITH HER, TRUSTING HER,
DEFENDING HER, EVERYTHING.
SERIOUSLY, MY BAD, ALL RIGHT?
YEP.
THAT'S IT? "YEP"?
I'M TRYING TO BE REAL WITH YOU.
I APPRECIATE THAT,
BUT IT DOESN'T TAKE AWAY
FROM THE FACT
THAT WE ARE DRIVING INTO THE
WOODS TO FIGHT POISON IVY,
WHO RENEE FREED AND
PROBABLY TOLD EVERYTHING TO,
MY IDENTITY, OUR PLAN,
OUR VULNERABILITIES.
WHOA! LOOK OUT!
YOU HAVE TO HELP ME! PLEASE!
OH, MY GOD!
YOU'RE OK. WE GOT YOU.
WE NEED TO GET OUT OF HERE!
- WE'RE NOT SAFE.
- WAIT. WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHO DID THIS TO YOU?
SOPHIE!
CRAP!
RUN!
UGH!
I C... I CAN'T.
NO. WE HAVE TO KEEP MOVING.
COME ON, COME ON.
LUKE, GUN!
GUN, GUN!
OK. LUKE, WE GOT TO GO.
WE GOT TO GO!
LUKE, WE GOT TO GO!
GUYS, THE CABIN. LET'S GO!
NOW WHAT?
LUKE.
LUKE!
YOU WANT TO TELL US
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WELL, WE JUST SAW
AN INNOCENT MAN
GET IMPALED WITH A ROOT,
SO 3 GUESSES.
THAT WASN'T YOUR FAULT.
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
HOW DO YOU NOT GET THAT?
OK. WHAT IS
THE COMMON DENOMINATOR
OF ALL OF OUR PROBLEMS?
THE BATWING SUIT
BREAKS HALF THE TIME
BECAUSE OF ME.
WE COULDN'T SAVE MARY
FROM POISON IVY
BECAUSE OF ME.
A FREAKING VINE SNAGGED
THE DART GUN AWAY
BECAUSE OF ME.
MY DAD KNEW ALL ALONG.
THERE WAS ONE REASON
HE DIDN'T GIVE ME THE SUIT
AND ONE REASON ONLY.
I AM NOT A HERO.
YOU KNOW HOW YOU'RE ON THE
JOURNEY TO BEING A HERO?
YOU FAIL.
I MEAN, LOOK AT SOPHIE.
ALICE AND PAM BOTH
ESCAPED ON HER WATCH,
AND SHE WORKED SECURITY
FOR 5 YEARS.
TRUE... AND RYAN, THE
SUPPOSED TEAM DETECTIVE,
DIDN'T EVEN NOTICE
THAT HER ROOMMATE
WAS INFECTED WITH POISON IVY
UNTIL IT WAS WAY TOO LATE.
TALK ABOUT SCREWING UP BIG TIME.
- SEE? NO ONE'S PERFECT.
- HMM.
YOU CAN'T SPIRAL ON US.
WE NEED YOUR OBNOXIOUSLY
SUPERIOR BRAIN
TO GET US OUT OF HERE.
ALL RIGHT. WELL, SHOTGUN,
HANDFUL OF SHELLS,
VINEGAR, BAKING SODA,
A SAW, AND A WHOLE BUNCH
OF OTHER CRAP FROM THIS CABIN.
YOU THINK YOU CAN FIGURE OUT
ANOTHER WAY TO TAKE HER DOWN?
I CAN TRY.
I TAKE IT YOU DIDN'T FIND MARY.
I HAD OTHER COMPANY.
WHAT DID YOU DO?
HOW DID BATWOMAN KNOW
WHERE I'D BE?
PAM...
ANSWER ME RIGHT NOW.
WHAT DID YOU DO?
THEY'RE FINE,
BUT NOW YOU'VE GOT ME
WONDERING WHY
YOU'RE SO CONCERNED.
THEY'RE NOT BAD PEOPLE.
BATMAN BURIED ME ALIVE.
I TOLD YOU RYAN IS NOT BATMAN.
AND WHAT DO YOU THINK
SHE'S GONNA DO TO ME?
- LET ME TALK TO HER.
- AND TELL HER WHAT?
THAT YOU CAN CHANGE.
I'M SORRY, PAM, FOR HURTING YOU.
I WILL REGRET WHAT I DID
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE,
BUT YOU CAN'T KEEP
GOING DOWN THIS PATH.
I WANT YOU TO BE
HEALTHY AND SAFE.
I WANT US TO BE ABLE TO HEAL
AND LEAVE THIS CITY BEHIND.
CAN I ALONE BE WORTH IT?
OF COURSE YOU'RE WORTH IT.
AND ONE DAY, WE WILL
LEAVE THIS CITY BEHIND US...
BUT RIGHT NOW,
I NEED TO MAKE SURE
NO ONE'S STANDING IN MY WAY.
STAY PUT.
DON'T MOVE A MUSCLE.
I'M GOING TO KILL BATWOMAN,
AND THEN WE CAN WORK ON US.
LOOKS LIKE THE CITY
DOESN'T HAVE MUCH HOPE
FOR THE ROGUES UNIT.
SHE'S NOT HERE.
YOU GOT A HAIRPIN
IN THAT FANCY THING?
THANK YOU.
GIVE ME.
YOU CAN TAKE THE GIRL
OUT OF THE STREETS,
BUT YOU CAN'T TAKE THE
STREETS OUT OF THE GIRL.
YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED
ONE BIT, HAVE YOU, JADA?
HEH.
I GOT BACK WITH MY WIFE.
LUCKY HER.
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE
IN THE RIGHT PLACE.
LIKE YOU SAID,
THESE BELONGED TO BATMAN,
THEN SOMEHOW MANAGED
TO FALL INTO THE RIVER
AND INTO THE HANDS
OF WOULD-BE KILLERS.
I THINK A CERTAIN HERO HAS
SOME EXPLAINING TO DO.
GREAT.
I FEEL BETTER SINCE WE TURNED.
OK. GOOD. YEAH.
SANTORINI, HERE WE COME.
UGH! AGH!
OK. ATTACK. TURN BACK.
COME ON. DO YOU WANT
TO RUN OUT OF GAS?
ALICE... I'M SERIOUS.
STOP THE CAR.
NO.
- I SAID STOP!
- OH! UGH!
UNH!
STOP! I AM SUPPOSED
TO BE THE CRAZY ONE!
YOU'RE NOT THE ONE WITH
A BITCH OF A MIGRAINE
THAT ONLY SEEMS TO STOP
BITCHING WHEN I GO...
THIS WAY!
IF YOU GO THAT WAY,
YOU'LL PROBABLY DIE!
THE O.G.'s BACK?
SHE'S TRYING TO DRAW YOU TO HER.
- WHY?
- UH, DO I LOOK LIKE
THE PRESIDENT
OF THE POISON IVY FAN CLUB?
I DON'T KNOW, BUT I DO KNOW
THAT A WORLD WITH TWO OF
A KIND NEVER ENDS WELL.
WHY DON'T YOU ASK
POOR, BORING BETH KANE?
OH, THAT'S RIGHT. YOU
CAN'T BECAUSE SHE'S DEAD!
OK. THEN THAT'S WHY I'VE
BEEN FEELING THIS WAY?
CLEARLY... W-W-WE HAVE
SOME SORT OF BOND,
AND SHE'S CALLING OUT TO ME.
GIVE ME THE KEYS.
WERE YOU NOT LISTENING
TO ANYTHING I SAID?
I'M GOING, ALICE.
THIS IS THE WOMAN WHO
UNLOCKED MY PROWESS
AND THE REASON WHY
I'M FINALLY HAPPY.
THE LEAST I CAN DO IS GO
AND SEE WHAT SHE WANTS.
PLEASE.
FINE. LET'S GO MEET YOUR MAKER.
TEQUILA?
IS THIS THE PART
WHERE I SAY, "YES,"
AND YOU PASS IT TO LUKE?
IT'S WHERE I THANK YOU
FOR GRABBING MY BATSUIT
WHILE YOUR CAR WAS
BEING SUCKED INTO THE ABYSS.
YOU'RE A BADASS.
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM WITH ME?
HEY. I HAVEN'T BROUGHT UP
RENEE ONCE SINCE WE GOT HERE.
I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT RENEE,
AND YOU CAN PRETEND ALL YOU WANT
THAT OUR PROBLEMS STARTED
WHEN SHE CAME INTO OUR LIVES,
BUT IT'S BEEN LIKE THIS
SINCE THE BEGINNING.
OH, YOU MEAN BACK WHEN YOU
THOUGHT I WAS A COMMON CRIMINAL?
IS THAT WHY YOU DON'T LIKE ME?
I HAVE APOLOGIZED, I'VE CHANGED.
RYAN, I LITERALLY
QUIT MY JOB IN PART
BECAUSE OF THIS RELATIONSHIP
AND WHAT I LEARNED FROM YOU.
I'M TRYING, OK,
BUT I'M NOT GETTING
ANYTHING IN RETURN.
WHAT DO YOU WANT IN RETURN?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?!
- OHH.
- LOOK. NO OFFENSE,
BUT, SOPHIE, I HAVE
SO MUCH GOING ON
IN MY HEAD RIGHT NOW,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I WANT.
YOU THINK?
HALF THE TIME, I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU LIKE ME OR HATE ME,
AND HONESTLY, I THINK
YOU'RE JUST AFRAID.
- AFRAID OF WHAT?
- OF FEELING SOMETHING REAL
AND BLOWING IT.
SO WHAT IS IT?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- SOPH!
- AAH! OHH!
- MOVE.
- WHAT?!
MOVE!
SALT AND VINEGAR.
WHY ARE WE WHISPERING?
IMAGINE EACH
OF THE TRILLION SPORES
IN THESE WOODS AS ONE OF
POISON IVY'S SENSORY GLANDS.
SHE CAN SENSE SOUND VIBRATIONS.
YEAH. SO BETWEEN THE HAMMERING
AND... THE ARGUING...
WE DREW HER RIGHT TO US.
WELL, GAME ON, BITCH.
LOAD UP TWO MORE OF THOSE.
WE'RE GOING
ON A POISON IVY HUNT.
I WISH I COULD,
BUT UNFORTUNATELY,
THAT WAS THE LAST OF THE SALT.
WAIT. ACTUALLY, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I SAW A BAG OF ICE
MELT IN THE TRUCK
IN THE DRIVEWAY.
THE TRUCK IN THE DRIVEWAY
OUTSIDE, OUT THERE
ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THESE WALLS?
OR WE CAN JUST
STAY COOPED UP IN HERE
AND SECOND-GUESS
EACH OTHER TO DEATH,
SAVE PAM THE EFFORT.
OK. UM, WE COULD DRAW
STRAWS TO SEE WHO GOES.
I'LL SAVE US THE TROUBLE.
I'M BATWOMAN.
I'LL GO.
SHE'S CLOSE.
I CAN FEEL HER WARM PULL.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WELL, SHE NAMED HERSELF
POISON IVY.
WHY NOT DELICATE LILAC
OR DAINTY LILY?
MAYBE BECAUSE SHE'S
A MASS MURDERER!
ALICE, WE ARE NOT TIRE IRONING
THE WOMAN RESPONSIBLE
FOR MY AWAKENING.
LOOK. AHEM.
I GET THIS WHOLE BONE OF MY
BONE, FLESH OF MY FLESH THING
THAT'S HAPPENING RIGHT NOW,
BUT, UH, THIS ISN'T ENDING
WITH THE TWO OF YOU WINDING
YOUR LITTLE VINES TOGETHER
AND MAKING A PEACE WREATH.
ARE YOU JEALOUS? WHAT... WHAT
IS HAPPENING HERE?
WHAT ARE YOU SO WORRIED ABOUT?
YOU ENDING UP DEAD!
BECAUSE THE, UM,
TICKETS TO SANTORINI
ARE... IN YOUR NAME,
AND IF YOU DIE,
I WILL MISS OUT
ON THE SPA RETREAT, SO...
WHY DO WE WORK, ALICE?
YOU KILLED MY MOM,
I REPLACED YOU IN OUR FAMILY,
BUT...
HERE WE ARE ON THIS
CRAZY ADVENTURE TOGETHER.
HMM? WHY?
PROBABLY BECAUSE YOU MADE ME DRIVE
OUT TO "DELIVERANCE" COUNTRY.
IT'S BECAUSE DESPITE
ALL OF OUR BAGGAGE,
WE BOTH FOUND THE
SISTER WE ALWAYS WANTED.
I SEE THE GIRL WHO...
JUST CRAVES HER FREEDOM,
AND I LOVE THAT YOU SUPPORT ME
TO DO WHAT I WANT...
AND THIS IS WHAT I WANT.
OK.
I HATE TO HAVE TO PULL
THIS CARD, SIS,
BUT, UM... TOUGH BEANS.
I'M OLDER.
ALICE... STOP.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU'RE STAYING RIGHT HERE.
I'M GOING ALONE.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA STOP ME.
NIGHTY NIGHT.
FINALLY MAKING YOURSELF USEFUL.
WELL, THEY HAD NO BORDEAUX
IN THAT MINI FRIDGE OVER THERE.
LET'S SEE IF SHE HAS
AN OPENER ROUND HERE.
SO HOW'D SHE FIND YOU?
YOUR DAUGHTER.
DAUGHTER?
I'VE NEVER ACTUALLY HEARD
HER DESCRIBED TO ME THAT WAY.
WELL, IF YOU DON'T
MIND ME ASKING,
WHAT'S KEEPING YOU FROM
TREATING HER THAT WAY?
LOOK AT ME, JOHN.
I JUST BROKE INTO CITY HALL
TO FIND A WAY TO KEEP
MY SON FROM BECOMING
ANOTHER MONSTER ON A CORK BOARD.
THE CLOSER I GET TO RYAN,
THE FASTER SHE BECOMES
A POTENTIAL VICTIM.
AND YET YOU SMILED JUST NOW
WHEN I BROUGHT UP HER NAME.
I ACTUALLY DON'T KNOW
HOW SHE FOUND ME, BUT...
MAYBE THERE'S A PART OF ME
THAT'S HAPPY THAT SHE DID.
WELL, MAYBE... HEAR ME OUT HERE...
JUST MAYBE IF YOU
DROPPED YOUR GUARD
FOR A MINUTE
AND OPENED YOURSELF UP
TO OTHER POSSIBILITIES,
THAT THING YOU THOUGHT WOULD
BE YOUR WORST NIGHTMARE
MIGHT JUST BE THE BEST THING
THAT EVER HAPPENED TO YOU, JADA.
FORGET THAT BEER, JOHN.
WE'RE GONNA NEED
THAT BORDEAUX AFTER ALL.
WE'RE CELEBRATING.
HEY. WHERE'S PAM?
I CAN'T LET YOU FIND HER.
GOOD LUCK.
HERE I AM TRYING TO TEACH
YOU AN IMPORTANT LIFE SKILL,
AND YOU'RE MORE
INTERESTED IN MY PHONE.
MOMMY SAID WE HAVE TO
MAKE MEM-OH-WEES.
MEMORIES, BUD, BUT
YOUR MOTHER IS RIGHT...
AHH... AS ALWAYS. HEH.
HEY.
STAY WHERE YOU ARE.
OH.
HEY. HEY. HELLO?
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED
TO YOU, GIRL?
- GET AWAY FROM ME!
- WHOA, WHOA!
AAH!
DAD!
WHAT IS SHE DOING?
HER DAMN ARMS
AREN'T LONG ENOUGH.
RYAN, ON COMMS: I CAN HEAR YOU.
I CAN'T WATCH.
IF YOU COULD GRAB BOTH,
THAT'D BE EVEN BETTER.
YOU GRAB BOTH.
OK. ONE IT IS.
WHAT IN THE ACTUAL HELL?
BATWOMAN, HELP!
OH, MY GOD.
RUN!
OHH!
LUKE, GET READY TO RUN.
- SOPHIE, I NEED YOU!
- TALK TO ME.
- BLOW UP THE TRUCK.
- WHAT?!
YOU ASKED ME WHAT I WANTED.
BLOW UP THE TRUCK.
THE SUIT WILL PROTECT ME.
WE DON'T KNOW THAT.
BLOW UP THE DAMN TRUCK!
HOW THE HELL AM I SUPPOSED TO...
SHOOT IT, HOTSHOT!
HEY. HEY. YOU GOOD?
YOU SAVED ME.
HERE YOU GO.
HEY. THE PARK RANGERS
ARE LOOKING FOR YOUR DAD,
AND THEY'RE GONNA FIND HIM, OK?
SOPHIE, CHECKING IN.
ANY SIGN OF HER?
RYAN. RYAN!
LUKE, I FOUND HER. SHE'S ALIVE.
UGH. I'M OK. UGH. I'M FINE.
FINE? THAT'S ALL
YOU HAVE TO SAY?
YOU ALMOST DIED.
SHE'S TOO STRONG FOR US.
WE NEED TO MAKE IT HOME,
MAKE A REPLICA OF LUKE'S GUN,
AND... AND FIND SOME MORE
OF THAT SERUM.
RYAN, LOOK AT ME.
NEVER PUT ME IN THAT
POSITION AGAIN.
IT STOPPED HER, DIDN'T IT?
- YOU COULD HAVE DIED!
- YEAH, BUT I DIDN'T.
BUT YOU COULD HAVE.
OH, WELL!
WHAT?! RYAN, NO.
YOU DON'T GET TO "OH,
WELL" ME AND WALK AWAY.
WHAT IS GOING ON WITH YOU?
I'M FREAKING EXHAUSTED, SOPHIE.
YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT I WANT?
I WANT TO SLEEP.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
I HAVE A FAMILY I DIDN'T ASK FOR
TRYING TO DESTROY MY CITY,
MY... MY BEST FRIEND
IS OFF THE GRID
BECAUSE I'VE BEEN SO PREOCCUPIED
I DIDN'T NOTICE SHE WAS
AN ENTIRELY DIFFERENT PERSON,
AND NOW A BATMAN SUPERVILLAIN
JUST KICKED ALL OF OUR ASSES,
SO, YEAH, THE THOUGHT
OF BLOWING UP
IN A FIERY EXPLOSION HONESTLY
SOUNDS LIKE A VACATION TO ME...
MAYBE THAT'LL GET YOU
OUT OF YOUR HEAD.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
TO LOOK FOR MY DAMN CAR.
♪ COLD BONES
OK. THEN.
♪ YEAH, THAT'S MY LOVE
A FRIEND OF MINE
TOLD ME THIS WORKED FOR HER,
SO I FIGURED WHAT THE HELL?
LOOK, DAD.
I GET WHY YOU DON'T THINK
I'M READY TO BE BATWING
BECAUSE YOU AND I
AND A WHOLE LOT
OF O.R. DOCTORS KNOW
THAT I'M NOT
EVEN SUPPOSED TO BE HERE
RIGHT NOW.
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE
IN THE GROUND NEXT TO YOU
WITH A SEVERED VEIN
AND 3 RUPTURED ORGANS,
BUT... THANKS TO SOME LUCKY,
IMPOSSIBLE, FREAK MIRACLE,
I'M NOT.
I'M STILL HERE.
BUT WHAT IF...
WHAT IF IT WASN'T
A FREAK MIRACLE?
WHAT IF YOUR DEATH WASN'T
A TRAGEDY?
WHAT IF ALL
THESE HORRIBLE THINGS
THAT HAPPENED TO ME
HAPPENED FOR A REASON?
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT
I'M STARTING TO THINK,
AND...
AS HARD AS IT IS TO SAY,
I CAN'T KEEP CARING
ABOUT WHAT YOU WOULD THINK
BECAUSE... DAD, I'M READY,
AND I LOVE YOU, AND I MISS YOU,
BUT...
I CAN'T LET YOU
HOLD ME BACK ANYMORE.
YOUR FATHER
WOULD BE PROUD OF YOU.
HEY. SORRY, MAN.
I TRIED, BUT I CAN'T
GET IT OPEN.
AW, DAMN IT.
GOT THAT SAME LINE
FROM A.R.G.U.S.
FIGURED I HAD A FIGHTING
CHANCE WITH YOUR BATTECH.
TO BE HONEST,
I DON'T ACTUALLY HAVE
ACCESS TO OUR BEST
RESOURCES AT THE MOMENT,
BUT FROM WHAT I CAN TELL,
THE TECHNOLOGY USED
ON A TRANSMATTER CUBE
PROBABLY ISN'T
FROM AROUND HERE, IS IT?
WHICH IS WHY I'D APPRECIATE
YOU KEEPING THIS BETWEEN US.
HOW'D YOU GET IT OPEN LAST TIME?
THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
IT JUST OPENED FOR ME.
SO MAYBE THE KEY
TO OPENING THAT BOX
ISN'T BASED ON SCIENCE,
HUMAN OR OTHERWISE.
MAYBE IT'S...
SOMETHING ELSE ENTIRELY.
YEAH.
NEED YOU TO DO
ONE MORE FAVOR FOR ME.
- OK. WHAT'S THAT?
- GET A MESSAGE TO BATWOMAN.
LET HER KNOW THAT JADA JET
FOUND A FIX.
SHE'S READY TO SAVE HER SON.
SINCE WHEN IS IT DAY?
HELLO. WHAT THE HELL
HAPPENED TO YOU, GIRL?
- GET AWAY FROM ME!
- WHOA, WHOA!
DAD!
OH, LITTLE SISTER...
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
LET'S JUST CALL THIS WHAT IT IS.
A TOXIC RELATIONSHIP.
HOW ARE YOU HERE? I... I...
PHEROMONED MY ASS? I KNOW.
I WAS THERE.
WHEN I THOUGHT THERE WAS
A CHANCE I'D SEE YOU AGAIN,
I CREATED A TOXIN,
STARTED INGESTING A DROP A DAY,
HOPING I COULD BUILD UP
A TOLERANCE
TO YOUR MIND CONTROL.
I GUESS YOU COULD SAY
I WAS AFRAID YOU'D DO
EXACTLY WHAT YOU ENDED UP DOING.
YOU DON'T LOVE ME.
I DO LOVE YOU, PAM.
I JUST DON'T LOVE YOU THE
WAY YOU WANT ME TO LOVE YOU.
THEN THAT'S NOT LOVE.
IT'S JUDGMENT,
AND MAYBE THIS IS
A TOXIC RELATIONSHIP.
I'VE SEEN ADDICTS WEEN
THEMSELVES OFF OF HEROIN
FASTER THAN WHAT WE'RE
DOING TO EACH OTHER.
WHAT DO YOU THINK KEPT ME ALIVE
FOR 10 YEARS, RENEE?
I HAD NO WATER,
NO SUNLIGHT,
NO HUMAN CONTACT.
I THOUGHT I WAS
GOING TO DIE THERE,
SO WHAT SINGLE THOUGHT
DO YOU THINK
I HELD ONTO FOR
EVERY WAKING MOMENT
OF EVERY BRUTAL DAY?
YOU.
SO... IF LOVING YOU THROUGH
EVERYTHING WE'VE BEEN THROUGH
IS TOXIC, THEN FINE.
WE'RE TOXIC. WALK AWAY,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
I'LL EVER LET YOU GO.
♪ CRY WOLF
YOUR SPORELING IS
STRONGER THAN EXPECTED.
ARE YOU GONNA LET ME DO THIS
OR STAND IN OUR WAY?
♪ BE THERE
♪ EAGER
♪ AND WILLING
♪ TO TAKE YOU INTO CARE
♪ YOU LIKE TO THINK
IT'S IN YOUR HEAD ♪
♪ COME TO FIND
IT'S IN YOUR BLOOD ♪
YOU FOUND ME.
NO.
♪ SO IN LOVE, WE'RE SO IN LOVE ♪
♪ AND IF SOMEDAY
THAT CRY SHOULD BREAK ♪
♪ THEN I WANT YOU TO REALIZE
IT'S A FAKE ♪
♪ HE'LL SINK HIS TEETH
INTO YOUR FLESH ♪
♪ AND YOU WILL WISH YOU NEVER
♪ CRIED WOLF
WHOA.
GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD!