Previously on Batwoman...
Mr. Freeze's liquid nitrogen can
got in the hands of a bunch
of 8th graders.
I need to find it.
Exposure to the freeze serum
will stop time
and keep you from aging.
Gonna need a little help.
Batwoman!
Ryan, wake up!
Not much left but Renee
was willing to cross it off her list.
Guess it's safe to say
you figured out the glitches
- in your super suit.
- You could say that.
It's because he disabled
the failsafe.
I shouldn't have cleared you
for field duty.
If you continue to try to have
anything to do with my family
you and Wayne Enterprises will come
to severely regret that decision.
Does that happen a lot?
Those delusions?
So you think you know my story.
Twenty-seven.
Raised in the system,
spend time at Blackgate.
Oh, and you're my sister.
Subject FXJ-1, re-animation
progress check, final phase.
You're free to go.
Re-animation failure,
24 hours until client deadline.
What the hell?
When did it get here?
Tragically early.
Delivery dude woke me out of bed.
Okay. Yeah. This is bad.
Yeah, but the picture's kind of cute.
Thirty Under Thirty. Yours truly?
I mean, I need to hang this up.
- Give me the note.
- Here.
You're welcome, fam.
See you at the press junket.
Marquis.
Your brother got you on the list?
First of all, I'm a rising star.
But also he used to hook up
with the editor of The Gazette, so...
So you now have a public date,
in front of the cameras
with the brother that
you have to stay away from
otherwise Jada Jet comes knives
out for you, Wayne Enterprises
maybe even your secret identity.
I tried to ghost him, okay?
But the word is out,
and Gotham is curious.
You know Charlie Clarke, right?
- Head of PR for Wayne?
- Yeah, of course.
Charlie has been with Wayne
since my dad was still there.
He is one of Bruce's
inner circle guys.
Okay, well, Charlie
has gotten dozens of requests
to interview Wayne's hot young CEO,
their words, not mine
and he says that
if I skip on this event
we're gonna have reporters trying
to climb the walls of Wayne Tower
to get answers.
Okay.
What's your plan for
when you run into Marquis?
Feel the shoulder.
Come on, feel it.
- Cold as they come.
- Okay.
Look, if I need a convo blocker,
Sophie's gonna be there.
Her sister is on the list
for the community center.
Oh, that is legitimately cool.
Great, you both are here.
Can I run something crazy by you?
My sweet girl, did you go home
with a boy last night?
No, see that's the thing.
I'm pretty sure
I spent the night asleep on a bench
in the middle of Gotham Park.
So, busy morning. I should jet.
Pun intended. Good luck.
Would Luke still be this upset
if nothing was actually wrong?
Luke is just frustrated.
You told me his PTSD
made him a risk in the field.
He just wants us to be able
to know we can depend on him.
Depend on him?
You mean like when you walk
into a room and say
"Hey, something really weird
just happened to me.
Can we talk about it?"
He'll come around, okay?
But I'm here to listen.
I have a jam-packed day.
So can we walk and talk?
Please?
Then we should just table my drama
because I sort of need
an active listener here.
Okay. How about this?
I'll buy drinks for happy hour,
then you can unload?
Sure, I'll just journal until then.
All right. Just breathe.
It's not like you're in
Norman Bates' psych wards
with a billion non-consensual
nanobots
swimming through your bloodstream.
Oh, wait.
You've got mail.
I hate that I'm old enough
to know what you did there.
It's from Daddy.
They all are.
An entire stack from old jail crow
Jacob Kane.
These misdeliveries
are from the weepy Post Office
inside my sick mind.
Now that sounds like a you problem.
Excuse me?
Help?
Kane?
What's the problem?
Everything looks normal to you?
Room inspections are Tuesdays
and Thursdays.
- What?
- I...
Just one more thing.
I really need to speak
with Renee Montoya.
Let's keep things moving, Charlie.
I want to make an impression,
and then leave them wanting more.
Great news,
the Chairman of Apex Broadcasting
got an eel bone stuck in his throat
so there is a photo session
slot available.
Lead the way.
Wayne Enterprises is set
to make its biggest quarterly
revenue gains in six years.
I had to bribe Mr. Wayne
with Bloody Marys
just to get him
to memorize his talking points.
- Ryan.
- Ryan, over here.
Over here.
Miss Wilder.
Ryan, over here.
Over here. Ryan, over here.
You wanna let me work?
I can barely tell you're smiling.
Come on, show Gotham
that new fire that's taking over.
- Ms. Wilder.
- Ryan.
Thank you so much.
Isn't she wonderful, folks?
That's Marquis Jet.
I want the cameras
to get a shot of you together.
The Jets are icons in this city.
Why are you avoiding me?
I thought that
once I got you on this list
you knew what I wanted...
- To piss off your mom?
- Yeah.
I'm just making up
for the missed time
you had with our mom
and the rebellious phase.
It's manipulative, and frankly,
it puts my business at risk.
- Look, Ryan...
- Hey, guys, can I get a smile?
I will be real with you.
I just wanted to do a nice thing
and hopefully have a chance
to hang out with my sister
but if that's too risky for you...
You're off the hook.
I gotta take this.
This is like the publicist
Hunger Games.
Did you see the sign at the bar
that says the free champagne
is for nominees only?
You want me to get you a glass
you should've bought me that
box of wine I wanted in college.
Okay, as your big sister,
I stand behind that decision.
It's as on-brand for me as being
here today is off-brand for you.
As an honoree, I get
a little speech at the party later.
Two minutes, anything I want to say.
My plan is to serenade
these moneybags
into quadrupling
the community center's budget.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime shot,
right?
That's my Under 30 bestie.
Always got her eye
on the prize and...
It must run in the family.
I have something embarrassing
to tell you.
I am so in.
- I had a dream about Ryan.
- Okay.
- I was in bed...
and I must have been sick
because she brought me some soup.
What kind of soup?
I woke up before I could even try it.
What?
You woke up early,
it's a classic dream about longing.
I knew you really liked her.
Why did I tell you this?
Okay, Jordan,
it wasn't a sexual dream, at all.
Did Ryan bring up a flower
with the soup?
- Told you.
- Okay.
I'm 31, I have no career
and I'm surrounded
by all you sick little prodigies
and my brain is begging me
"Hey, loser,
can you at least find a girlfriend?"
But that doesn't mean
it has to be Ryan.
Or, and hear me out on this.
Ryan Wilder is hot as hell,
and you're amazing together.
You're staring again. I just...
You know what? I have to go.
I'll be right back
- To the bathroom?
- Just worry about your speech.
Jordan Moore? I'm from The Gazette.
We're ready
to sit for your interview.
Okay, sure, let me just grab
my publicist.
- That won't be necessary.
- Hey...
Vesper Fairchild is holding.
Vesper, it's Jada.
I happened to glance
at last week's ratings, ouch.
It's a crowded landscape, my dear.
But I want to help you
make some noise.
Yes, I have a scoop.
Explain this new hobby to me.
Only if you explain why Montoya
dropped you off for me to babysit.
I have urgent information
to help Batwoman recover
the infamous "zero-G sneakers."
Used by Batman's long-ago fallen
and tragically arrogant foe,
the Mighty Icarus!
Icarus?
Sounds like a deep cut.
Actually, it's fake,
but she'll believe anything
if you lower your voice an octave.
It's convincing, right?
Convince me not to tell Montoya
that there is no Mighty Icarus.
Well for one, you're lonely.
Well then maybe we could do
each other's nails
or try a few elective surgeries.
There has to be some reason
why you're playing hooky from Arkham.
Well, I hate to admit anything
that would make me sound weak
but the truth is...
I'm here to do Batwoman a favor.
Well, keep going, so far this story
is better than your nanobot cold.
First things first,
can you tell me what trophy
the Bat Team
is heroically tracking down
at this very moment
to keep the Gotham streets safe
and appease the tyrant
that is forcing us to work together?
Something came up.
We'll get back
to Renee's treasure hunt tomorrow.
No judgment here
but I wonder if Renee
would be as generous
toward this work-life balance?
I guess you'll find out
when you call her.
Fine, you win.
Just don't bother anyone
who comes in.
I can't believe
you've never had media training.
Just highly motivated. Who's next?
Let me shoot The Gazette
a quick text
and see if they're ready for you.
Figured you'd chill
if I bought a disguise
so they had this sick colorway
at the gift shop.
"Who's that man with Ryan Wilder?
Is he handsome?
I can't tell!"
Yeah, you probably
should have got some aviators.
I should've. They're two for one.
You want in?
Hey, Ryan, have you seen Jordan?
She's late for an interview,
and her phone is off.
Never let the client
out of your sight.
I'm more publisister
than publicist, so...
I would've guessed print model.
Cool hat.
Marquis Jet. I'm Ryan's brother.
Sophie Moore. Ryan's...
Very good friend who needs help
finding her baby sister.
The Gazette says
they're ready for you.
Can we push this off
until after the interview?
My girl comes first.
See if that dude got rid
of the eel bone yet.
Come on, let's go.
Okay. Re-booting voice interface.
Re-booting system loader.
Dad? It's Luke. Are you there?
The silent treatment is getting old.
Are you really gonna leave me hanging
with the most sophisticated
personal flight suit on the planet?
Is this about the failsafe?
You're mad because I turned it off?
Because that's on you,
it malfunctioned, so...
You know, and also
almost got me killed, so, no.
I'm not turning it back on.
My suit, my decision.
Batwoman to Batcave. You there?
Yup, just talking to my wardrobe,
having a normal one.
Batwoman, hey.
I thought you were taking
a personal day?
I need an assist.
Sophie's sister Jordan is MIA.
Too many mai tais at the open bar?
I hope not. I cleaned up
enough puke at my old job.
I got a ping from her cellphone.
Let me just narrow down
the location radius
with the hotel Wi-Fi.
Not to be a downer at a party
but it might be time to panic.
Was something going on with her?
She seemed nervous, but only
because she had a speech later.
Facial recognition says no Jordan
on any of the exterior hotel cams.
So she must still be on the premises.
Hey, I just got a tip
that your sister was spotted
upstairs at the hotel.
Some man brought her to room 1620.
Let's go.
Okay, you stay here. Keep an eye out.
Call me if she comes back down.
Jordan? Oh, my God.
No, don't touch her,
not until we know what happened.
Who the hell would do this to her?
I've seen this equipment before.
This is Mr. Fries' design.
Freeze serum did this?
I thought you said you got
that stuff off the streets.
I got the original canister back,
but maybe someone found more?
Why would they do this to Jordan?
And how are they doing this
without a cryo chamber?
You know what, I'll handle it.
- I have to move her...
- You cannot warm her, Sophie.
It's too dangerous.
The last time someone tried that
she aged at four times
the normal rate.
This is my sister, Ryan.
She's my responsibility.
I know.
We will figure this out together.
The catalytic mechanism is based
on Victor Fries' research
but what used to happen
inside a chamber
is now happening
inside Jordan's cells.
I just wanna know how to undo it.
Tell me how to help.
The main complication that we've seen
with Fries' cryo-stasis
is rapid aging.
But this is so much more invasive.
If I had to guess what this could do
to organic tissue?
Have you ever seen a piece
of petrified wood before?
We should just pause on that analogy
and just focus. What do you need?
Want me to go to the store
for a hairdryer?
Why the hell is Alice even here?
It's really
not even worth explaining.
Look, if I can get a clean sample
of this new freeze serum
I think I could figure out a safe way
to bring Jordan out of cryo.
Then we should find out who made it
and see if they have more.
Were they working with anyone
at the hotel?
Or with the event?
We should have Luke check
every camera system
- to see if he can pull...
- I got it.
It's the Bee Gees.
Of course, it's them.
Did you take my sister's phone?
Oh, yeah. And you're welcome.
For critiquing her taste in music?
No.
For solving
all your little mysteries.
Who kidnapped Jordan.
Who's experimenting
with the freeze formula.
Same answer.
The Black Glove Society.
The BGS.
The Bee Gees.
They rule the city from the shadows,
they want to live forever.
You know, the usual
big-money pervert stuff.
She's right.
Jordan and her friends
were collecting information
on some Black Glove Society.
She was going to use her speech
at the 30 Under 30
to unmask the society
and shut it down.
Now that is a great way
to make yourself a target
of Gotham's oldest secret society
of the rich and powerful.
I'll send this info to Luke
so he can check on the others
to see if they're okay.
Why didn't you tell me
what you were doing?
You? Special Agent Play-It-Safe?
She knew you'd try to talk her
out of it.
Mary, I don't think her temperature
is stable.
You're right.
The formula must be breaking down
inside of her body.
If I could just get a sample
of this formula
I can figure all of this out.
It's too bad we can't just ask her
on how to find the Bee Gees.
She was obviously close enough
to something
for them to turn her into a popsicle.
- Alice, you're coming with me.
- Where are you going?
I can't just wait for Ryan
to solve this for me.
We're gonna search
Jordan's apartment.
If she's got any other evidence
on Black Glove
it'll be hidden there.
I just got the Black Glove files
from Sophie.
Give me one second to see
what Jordan had on here.
Nothing they do is digital.
Maybe that's how
they stay off the radar.
No computers, nothing on the cloud...
Nothing we can use
to get a name or location?
What about the people Jordan
was texting earlier?
MIA. They all met at the hotel.
But then they all went dark.
I bet that's why Black Glove does
the freeze experiments at the hotel.
You know, one-stop shopping everyone
who has it out for them.
Oh, my God.
The coroner's taking someone
out of the hotel in pieces.
Probably one of Jordan's team.
Okay.
I'm going up to the hotel.
We gotta find the other one.
Did you have eyes on Marquis
around the time
that Jordan went missing?
- Why?
- BGS is big money.
You know, flashy guys doing
whatever it takes to stay powerful.
He would fit perfectly
into that crowd.
Find your friend's sister?
Yeah, I did. Thanks.
Right where you said she'd be.
I'm glad I could be of service.
I bet he is.
How did he know which room
Jordan was in in the first place?
How did you know where to find her?
I know a girl who works
at the front desk.
She asked around for me.
One of the housekeepers said
that she saw someone
who looked like Jordan
being led into a bedroom
by some older guy.
I'm not accusing you. Okay?
But like I said,
I don't really know you, Marquis.
- I actually came to apologize.
- For what?
You think Jada's crazy, angry,
control freak thing is something new?
This has been my whole life.
Only child.
I wanted to know you so bad.
And I thought, finally, my sister,
we got each other's backs.
But I guess not.
What the hell was that all about?
I'll figure it out
after we help Jordan.
Is your phone seriously
not on right now?
Charlie, sorry, she's on silent.
Look, I just ran into some movers
and shakers at the hotel
so I gotta get back to it, okay?
Look.
Ryan, why is he so pissed?
Built you up just so
I can knock you down.
Okay. Better give me
the executive summary.
Five minutes ago, Vesper Fairchild
broke a scoop
that the CEO of Wayne Enterprises
has been diverting
tens of millions of dollars
into secret accounts for her own use.
Jada...
I just got off the phone
with our CFO.
He's started doing an audit
of our accounting systems
and he agrees that there's a problem.
What? No.
It's not possible.
Okay, look. I will talk to him
and sort this out.
But just not right now.
Oh, do you have
a more desperate crisis?
They say multitasking
is the hardest part of the job.
Not for much longer.
Okay. Don't worry.
I will get a box
for my personal belongings.
Girl, when you catch Bernie Madoff,
in this case, you, stealing money
you don't fire her.
You arrest her.
Tell me something good, Luke.
Maybe, like, Jada Jet
hacked our systems
and faked all that hidden money.
Ryan, she didn't fake this.
Why am I the last person to know
that I have eight figures stashed
under a mattress somewhere?
Can you think of any operations that
are extremely expensive, secretive
and can only be authorized
by the CEO of Wayne Enterprises?
Batman. And now, Batwoman.
That money is our operating budget.
Look, I have no idea
how Jada got access
to our accounting systems, so...
The only good news is she
doesn't know what the money is for.
Just that she can pin it on you.
Luke, I give up.
There's nothing here.
The cops could walk in any second
and I'm freezing my ass off.
GCPD has thermal imaging cameras
all over the city.
Let me tap in
and see if any of the other rooms
have abnormal temperatures.
I'm not seeing any iceboxes.
Luke...
I'm seeing
a bunch of heat lamps here.
Maybe they were getting ready
to try thawing her?
If they did that in another room...
Then on thermal imaging,
it would look more like a sauna.
Okay, bingo. Get ready to suit up.
What's the situation?
Dead body.
They tried to unfreeze it.
Didn't work.
Positive ID. She's the other one
in Jordan's group text.
No sign of Black Glove.
Okay, I just ran the name
of the other guy in the group text.
According to the GCPD, he was the one
they just wheeled out of there.
Jordan's the only one left.
Hey, no sass. You lived in the sewer.
I'll take the bedroom.
Remember,
we're looking for anything low tech.
Anything connected to Black Glove.
Jordan knew it was dangerous,
so it won't be out in the open.
You shouldn't be here.
How's your neck?
That's hurtful.
Are you talking to someone?
Oh, no.
No, I just like
to say the details out loud.
Please respect my process
and go back to digging
through your sister's underwear
drawer or something
Go, go.
You want my two cents?
First of all, they're my two cents.
Second of all, shut up. I'm working.
You don't wanna read
those postcards.
You don't like
feeling those little machines
swimming around in you like guppies.
You broke my damn neck.
I'm sorry.
Do I seem a teensy bit on edge?
It's only because the fabric of
my reality is collapsing around me.
Are you sure
you're keeping it together in there?
Oh, yeah.
You know, just overcoming the mold
of your sister's dusty manifesto.
Maybe if you knew
what was real about yourself, Beth...
the rest of the world
would fall back into place.
She unmasked the Bee Gees.
That doesn't belong to you.
Thanks for the warning.
Just taking a shot here.
Are you make-believe?
I'm here for everything that was
scanned into the girl's phone.
Pro-tip.
Buy a document shredder.
What's up, Luke?
You didn't give us an update
on your progress with Jordan.
Listen, I'm trying to keep her stable
until someone comes through
with a sample of the formula.
You've had her long enough
to analyze every angle
run every test,
and you've still got nothing?
No pressure, huh?
If you get to judge me for how
I'm performing in the clutch
why can't I do the same for you?
I was trying to help you.
Not score points in some
"who's the best hero" competition.
Look, I'm not dunking on you.
I'm just reminding you that
you declared yourself team doctor.
Yeah, and I'm trying.
But I can barely see straight
because I spent the night
in the park.
Which nobody knows about
because nobody actually cares...
What is it?
I can hear.
You just got an idea, right?
Animals never evolved
to withstand freezing
but plants have organic material
that perfectly adapted
to freezing and thawing.
And they survive winter
by synthesizing
a type of anti-freeze
inside their vascular tissue.
The key is to thaw from the inside,
not the outside.
And you think this could be a way
to safely unfreeze Jordan?
No, I just thought
it was a fun fact about plants.
What's that smell?
Gasoline.
Alice. Alice!
What?
It hurts a little on the nose
but the books are a nice touch.
Hey, where's your knife?
The Bee Gees took it.
Along with all the evidence I found
in Jordan's hidey-hole.
Stop trying to make Bee Gees happen.
Geez. Misdirected anger, much?
Misdirected?
This is completely your fault.
What?
You're Alice, a legit supervillain.
The only reason these guys jumped you
is because you thought
you were talking to some guy
who wasn't even there.
Yeah, I noticed.
Sometimes, I...
I'm not sure what's real
and what's not
and it used to only happen in Arkham
but it's getting worse
and I don't know what to do.
And I don't have anyone
who wants to help me.
Oh, that's one way
to solve my problem.
Sorry, Jordan.
Hey, how are you feeling?
I wish you had told me.
I could've helped.
I will always support you, Jordan.
Always.
She'll need some more time
before she could talk again.
Her entire body is resetting.
I'm not gonna lie
she might smell like cilantro
for the next couple of days
but she's gonna make a full recovery.
Oh, thank goodness. Can we eat now?
I'm so sorry, Soph.
I said I'd handle this, and we still
don't know who these people are
or what they're doing
with the freeze serum.
Jordan's okay,
and that's all that matters.
So how did you know
to come to the apartment?
Luke figured out they were after
the original documents
Jordan had on her phone.
I'm not going to let Black Glove
get another shot at her.
Yeah, well, they almost burned me
at the stake.
So you're getting my help on this.
And Alice's too,
whether we want it or not.
Mary.
So Alice told me
her psychosis is getting worse
and she suspects
the doctors don't care.
Honestly?
It's Arkham.
Whatever meds
they're giving her in there
could be causing a psychotic break
instead of curing it.
It's going to be everyone's problem
if Alice fully loses her mind
before we finish the job for Montoya.
But, hypothetically, I could get
a supervised work release from Arkham
and sweet Mary could make sure
I was taking my proper meds.
I'm sure that Ry-Ry could convince
Renee-nay it was for the best.
You know, all for the sake
of "fighting crime."
Right, and who's going to put up
with that babysitting job?
Someone who sleeps with a gun
under her pillow.
What do you say? Roomies!
- How's the other crisis?
- Resolved.
So you'll be one-for-two today.
You might think you're here
to give me best practices
for a perp walk
but I'm not going anywhere.
I did nothing wrong.
Oh, I believe you.
You haven't been on the job
long enough to embezzle a stapler
let alone 30 million.
I think you made the wrong person
your enemy
and now you are the fall gal
for Bruce Wayne's misdeeds.
You think Bruce Wayne
stole from his own company?
Mr. Wayne's legacy
has been complicated
since he took over the company.
With his addictions, misbehaviors,
and disappearances, let's just say
I'm used to the challenge
of putting lipstick on a pig.
What's this?
Press release
that will go out in the morning.
After a thorough review, it was
determined that the "missing" money
was part of a top-secret
defense contract
that you negotiated with ARGUS.
CEO Wilder thought
no one could know about this
for national security reasons
and deeply regrets not alerting
the board of directors.
ARGUS is gonna go along
with the story?
I've got an old friend there.
He's doing me a favor.
Okay.
That's it? Crisis averted?
Unfortunately, no.
The stock price is still cratering
because someone
is coordinating a campaign
to undermine shareholder confidence.
If we don't do something
to restore confidence
we are at risk of a hostile takeover.
The board of directors
is demanding your resignation.
It is the best shot we have
at containing the crisis.
Okay, Charlie.
What do you think I should do?
That's up to you, Ms. Wilder.
But in my opinion
if you remain as CEO,
we will lose the company.
Well, we knew
she was capable of this.
Did we?
Because I'm not even clear why
the woman hates me so damn much.
I'm her daughter.
And I told you
that does not matter to her.
Okay, look...
Bruce was the face
of Wayne Enterprises
but my dad was his partner
and Bruce would always say
that the company belonged to Lucius
as much as it did him.
Ryan, I cannot lose this place.
You think I can?
What happens to Batwoman if there's
no cash to put gas in the Batmobile?
I am not letting Jada
take my calling.
So what, so even though
nobody thinks that you win
you're just gonna...
stay and fight?
Have you met me?
Okay.
Failsafe subroutine re-activated.
Now let's power cycle
the boot loader...
It's good to see you again, son.
Dad?
Oh, my God, I...
I really needed to hear your voice.
So the company's under attack
and I feel like
if we lose Wayne Enterprises
that's just another piece of you
that's gone from my life.
Helping Wayne Enterprises is beyond
the scope of what I can help with.
Yeah, I know,
we're already making a plan.
I just... I needed to know
why you stopped talking to me.
You repaired the system fault
in the O.S.
that had been blocking this A.I.
from normal operation.
I didn't repair anything.
I just turned the failsafe back on.
Lucas, this A.I. is not designed
to run independent of the failsafe.
It has no purpose
if it's not empowered to act
in your best interest.
Right, okay, so once a dad,
always a dad.
What did you want to ask me?
A friend of mine kind of already
gave me the answer, but...
I need to hear it
from the man himself.
I'm not ready to wear the suit, am I?
No, son.
You're not.
So why'd you had me meet you here?
Nothing left to lose?
Jada wants Wayne Enterprises,
doesn't she?
Look...
I'm sorry
you had to face Jada's wrath
and that I had something
to do with that
but she's had me sign
a thousand NDAs over the years
so I can't really talk
about company business.
What happened to siblings
having each other's backs?
What happened was
you weren't interested.
I am not letting our mom
take over Wayne Enterprises.
Do you think the two of us
could stand a chance against Jada...
if we pledge to work together?
It's deadline day, my friend.
What do you have for me?
I have the answer
you've been searching for.
And it works the way I asked?
It wasn't an easy process, but yes.
We were able to adapt Victor Fries'
research into a new formula
that can safely freeze
and unfreeze organic material.
What made the process so difficult?
Our arrangement is that
Black Glove Society commissions us
to achieve the impossible
but our terms were non-negotiable,
you do not inquire about our methods
nor our identities.
You don't want to tell me
what lines you crossed
to achieve the impossible.
You want to know what line I crossed?
The final breakthrough
came from a rival research team.
I stole their idea.
As long as that's the extent of it,
I'm a very happy customer.
There's nothing wrong
with a little corporate espionage.
So now that you have the ability
to put anyone's life on pause
indefinitely...
you just give me the word
and I'll make it happen.
Oh, I will,
and it won't be a long wait.
The time has come for my son Marquis
to take his leave of absence.