PREVIOUSLY ON "BATWOMAN"...
YOU'RE RESPONSIBLE
FOR EVERYTHING SHE DOES
UNTIL YOU TWO HAVE
TRACKED DOWN
EVERY LAST ONE
OF THOSE TOXIC TOYS
FROM BATMAN'S TROPHY CASE.
LUKE: RIGHT NOW,
A THOUSAND NANOBOTS
ARE SWIMMING THROUGH
YOUR BLOODSTREAM,
SENDING OUT TRACKING
BEACONS TO SATELLITES
AS WE SPEAK.
IF I'M READING
THIS RIGHT,
THE SUIT THOUGHT
YOU WERE INJURED.
WHICH PROMPTED
A SYSTEM-WIDE SHUTDOWN,
PUTTING THE SUIT
IN SAFE MODE.
I THOUGHT
YOU AND I AGREED
YOU'D STAY OUT
OF MY BUSINESS.
THIS IS PERSONAL...
BECAUSE I'M
YOUR DAUGHTER.
BUS DRIVER! WAIT!
BUS DRIVER, WAIT,
WAIT, WAIT!
WAIT, YOU PIECE OF--
I PAY TAXES!
I PAY YOUR SALARY, MAN!
SCREW YOU!
YO. WANT TO SEE
SOMETHING AWESOME?
TAYLOR, CHECK THIS OUT.
T, LOOK. I FOUND IT
CATCHING FROGS
UNDER LOEB BRIDGE.
SHH. I'M ABOUT TO
UNLOCK A PET.
-TAYLOR, COME ON.
-EVAN, CHILL.
TELL THEM I'M GONNA
BE LATE.
NO. I'M SORRY.
IT'S NOT MY--
YOU GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
I LOVE THIS FRICKING TOWN.
GOTHAM OFFICIALS HAVE
NO COMMENT
ON HOW A TANK
OF LIQUID NITROGEN
ENDED UP IN THE HANDS
OF SCHOOLCHILDREN
AND CAUSED THIS BUS TO FREEZE.
GOTHAM OFFICIALS ARE
LINKING THE FREEZING AGENT
TO MR. VICTOR FRIES,
THE DECEASED CRYOBIOLOGIST
GOTHAM REMEMBERS
AS ONE OF BATMAN'S
COLDEST ENEMIES.
MS. WILDER'S HERE
FOR YOUR MEETING, MS. JET.
DEWITT: OFFICIALS ARE ASKING
ANYONE WITH INFORMATION
AS TO WHERE THE FRIES SERUM
CAME FROM
TO CALL THE GCPD.
THAT'S WHY I TAKE
THE SUBWAY.
I'M SORRY WE DIDN'T
GET A CHANCE
TO FINISH
OUR CONVERSATION
LAST NIGHT.
I HAVE TO ADMIT
I NEVER PLANNED
ON MEETING YOU.
IT'S A LOT TO PROCESS.
I SEE YOU'VE RISEN
ABOVE YOUR CIRCUMSTANCES
TO GET YOUR DEGREE,
CLIMB THE CORPORATE
LADDER,
BECOME THE ACTING CEO
OF WAYNE.
YOU'VE TURNED YOURSELF
INTO A RATHER REMARKABLE
YOUNG WOMAN, RYAN.
THANK YOU.
LOOK.
I DIDN'T COME HERE
TO BLAME YOU
FOR ANYTHING.
YOU KNOW, WHATEVER
YOUR SITUATION WAS
AT THE TIME,
YOU WERE YOUNG
OR SCARED
OR IF I WAS UNPLANNED,
UNWANTED, WHATEVER,
NO JUDGMENT.
I JUST WANTED YOU TO KNOW
THAT IT'S ALL GOOD.
I TURNED OUT OK.
RYAN, IN AN EFFORT
TO RESPECT YOUR
TIME AND MINE,
I WILL TRY TO MAKE
THIS AS SIMPLE
AS POSSIBLE.
I'M NOT INTERESTED
I HAVING
A RELATIONSHIP
WITH YOU.
NOW IF YOU DON'T MIND,
I HAVE A MEETING
I NEED TO PREPARE FOR.
WAIT. WHY HAVE ME
AND THEN COVER IT UP?
ADAM, WILL YOU LET
BONNIE KNOW THAT
I'M ON MY WAY?
YOU PAID A DOCTOR
$2 MILLION TO FAKE
YOUR NAME
ON MY BIRTH CERTIFICATE
AND THEN MADE IT LOOK LIKE
YOU DIED SO I NEVER
CAME LOOKING FOR YOU.
WHAT WERE YOU
AFRAID OF?
SOMETIMES, IT'S
BETTER TO STOP
ASKING QUESTIONS.
SO YOU INVITED ME HERE
JUST TO SHOW ME THE DOOR?
IF YOU CONTINUE
TO TRY TO HAVE
ANYTHING TO DO
WITH MY FAMILY,
I WILL PERSONALLY
SEE TO IT THAT YOU
AND WAYNE ENTERPRISES
WILL COME TO SEVERELY
REGRET THAT DECISION.
I ALWAYS WONDERED
WHO MY BIRTH MOTHER WAS.
NOW I KNOW.
SOMEONE NOT WORTH MY TIME.
I'M GLAD WE'RE
ON THE SAME PAGE.
MAN: WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
I MISSED IT?
DAMN. SEE, THIS IS WHAT
I GET
FOR SECOND-GUESSING
MY KICKS.
I WENT DEEP VAULT
FOR YOU, WILDER.
WORTH IT?
I ACTUALLY USED TO HAVE
THOSE IN BLUE.
THERE YOU GO.
WORTH IT.
SEE, WE'RE
CONNECTING ALREADY.
MARQUIS, I THOUGHT
YOU WERE ON YOUR WAY
TO "METROPOLIS"
MAGAZINE'S
INFLUENCER PARTY
TONIGHT.
I WAS. THEN I HEARD
YOU WERE SITTING DOWN
WITH A NEW, YOUNG CEO
WITHOUT ME,
AND I FIGURED IT WAS
A SCHEDULING OVERSIGHT,
SO I BOUNCED.
I AM SORRY.
WHO ARE YOU?
YOU'RE NEW NEW.
THAT'S COOL.
I WON'T TAKE
ANY OFFENSE.
I'M JETURIAN INDUSTRIES'
EXECUTIVE VICE PRESIDENT.
MARQUIS JET.
ALSO KNOWN
AS MY SON.
YOU WERE VERY CLEAR
ABOUT KNOWING
THE ABSOLUTE MINIMUM.
YOU WEREN'T EVEN SURE
IF YOU WANTED TO GET
TO KNOW JADA,
SO KNOWING SHE HAD
ANOTHER KID,
IT WOULD HAVE JUST
COMPLICATED IT MORE.
THE KID SHE KEPT
WHILE SHE GAVE
ME AWAY.
WAS HE COOL
AT LEAST?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
JADA KICKED ME OUT
OF THERE SO FAST,
I DIDN'T EVEN GET
TO GET MY PARKING VALIDATED.
THIS IS EXACTLY WHY
I WANTED TO KEEP
THAT DOOR CLOSED.
-SO WHAT NOW?
-YOU DIDN'T HEAR?
MR. FREEZE'S
LIQUID NITROGEN CAN
GOT IN THE HANDS
OF A BUNCH OF EIGHT GRADERS.
I NEED TO FIND IT.
I MEAN ABOUT YOUR MOM.
WHAT CAN I DO?
WHAT DO YOU NEED?
MARY: YOU POOR THING.
-I'M SO SORRY, RYAN.
-THANKS.
IT SUCKS,
BUT...I'LL BE FINE.
OK. FIRST,
HOW DARE SHE,
AND SECOND, HOW'D YOU
KNOW SHE WAS STILL ALIVE?
OK. EVERYONE WAS LIKE,
"BOO-HOO.
EVIL ALICE KILLED
RYAN'S MOM."
AS IF IT WASN'T
BAD ENOUGH.
AND NOW AGAINST ALL ODDS,
I MIRACULOUSLY PROVIDE HER
WITH ANOTHER ONE,
AND YOU GUYS ARE JUST
BITCHING AND MOANING--
CAN I GET SOME WATER?
PLEASE, SOMEONE.
RYAN: OK. PLEASE TELL ME
YOU HAVE SOME INFO
ON THIS FREEZE STUFF.
SO THE CANISTER
ITSELF IS A COMPACT,
CUSTOM-BUILT
VACUUM FLASK
THAT MAKES ITS CONTENTS,
AKA THE FREEZE STUFF,
MORE CONCENTRATED
AND SEEMINGLY
LESS DANGEROUS THAN IT IS.
A LITTLE GOES
A LONG WAY.
SO THE KID LIKELY FOUND IT
NEAR THE GOTHAM RIVER,
THOUGHT IT WAS
A HARMLESS DRY-ICE GUN.
ALICE: ALL RIGHT.
I'M REALLY NOT FEELING WELL.
I THINK IT'S ALL THESE
TRACKING NANOBOTS
INSIDE ME.
MY SKIN, IT, UM,
FEELS LIKE SPIDERS ARE
RUNNING THROUGH MY VEINS.
OK. THAT'S NOT
A THING.
LUKE: WAYNE TECH USES
NANOBOT INJECTABLES
IN THEIR RESEARCH
ALL THE TIME.
RYAN: ARE YOU
CALLING IN SICK?
IS THAT WHAT THIS IS?
MONTOYA WANTS US
TO WORK TOGETHER.
MY TEAM GETS A BEAD
ON THE BATMAN TROPHY,
AND THEN YOU USE
YOUR CREEPY-ASS BRAIN
TO HELP US FIGURE OUT
WHERE IT IS.
AND I WOULD LOVE
NOTHING MORE TRULY
THAN TO TALK
ABOUT AN ERRANT CAN
OF LIQUID NITROGEN,
BUT I AM FINDING IT
VERY DIFFICULT TO FOCUS
THROUGH MY PAIN,
AND I WOULD HATE
MS. MONTOYA TO THINK
THAT OUR LITTLE ARRANGEMENT
DIDN'T WORK ON ACCOUNT
OF ME BEING IN A HOSTILE
WORK ENVIRONMENT.
RYAN: OH, MY GOD.
WHAT DID I DO
TO DESERVE THIS?
YOU KNOW, IT'S PROBABLY
NOT THE WORST THING
IF YOU GIVE ALICE
THE SICK DAY.
WHY DOES SHE GET
A DAY OFF?
BECAUSE I KNOW
WHERE THE CANISTER IS.
PLUS I DOUBT THAT
YOU'LL WANT
ONE OF GOTHAM'S
MOST WANTED WITH YOU
BREAKING INTO THE GCPD.
-I'M IN.
-COOL.
I CAN ONLY KEEP
THE CAMERAS DARK FOR 5 MINUTES,
SO START LOOKING.
YOU SURE IT'S HERE?
LOGS SAY IT WAS TAGGED
AND FILED AT 10:07 A.M.
THIS MORNING
NO RECORD OF ANYONE
REMOVING IT.
I THINK I KNOW WHY BATMAN
KEPT HIS OWN EVIDENCE LOCKER.
WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT DID
YOU DO?
I FOUND IT, NORA.
WE CAN FINALLY FINISH
WHAT VICTOR STARTED.
YOU STOLE VICTOR'S
FREEZE TANK?
NORA FRIES!
HA HA HA!
YOU ARE GONNA TELL ME
HOW YOU WERE FROZEN
FOR 20 YEARS...
AND LIVED TO
TALK ABOUT IT.
LUKE: I WAS ABLE TO COMPARE
ENTRY AND EXIT FOOTAGE
FROM THE TIME OF THE THEFT
AND TRACK DOWN
WHO BROKE INTO
THE EVIDENCE ROOM FIRST.
-ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
-DEE WORKS
AT THE GCPD
PROCESSING DESK.
SHE'S ONE OF A FEW PEOPLE
WHO HAVE ACCESS
TO THE EVIDENCE ROOM
SECURE BACK AREA.
DEE ALSO CALLED IN
SICK TODAY,
AND THIS LADY'S NEVER
CALLED IN SICK ONCE
IN 20 YEARS.
OK, BUT ALL THE ITEMS
IN THE EVIDENCE ROOM,
THERE HAS TO BE
SOMETHING EASIER
TO FENCE.
WHICH IS WHAT I THOUGHT.
WHY WOULD ANYONE
RISK EVERYTHING
FOR THIS STUFF APART
FROM THE GUY
WHO INVENTED IT?
WAIT. YOU MEAN
THE MR. FREEZE DUDE?
-I THOUGHT HE WAS DEAD.
-VICTOR FRIES. HE IS.
BRILLIANT CRYOBIOLOGIST,
HALF A DOZEN DOCTORATES,
STILL INSISTED ON BEING
CALLED MR. FREEZE,
BUT THEN AGAIN,
CAPTAIN COLD WASN'T
REALLY A CAPTAIN, SO...
WHO'S THAT?
AH, YES.
THAT IS NORA FRIES
IN AN ARKHAM INTAKE PHOTO
TAKEN 3 YEARS AGO.
SO NORA WAS DIAGNOSED
WITH MacGREGOR'S SYNDROME,
A PROGRESSIVE LUNG DISEASE
THAT AT THE TIME
OF HER DIAGNOSIS
HAD NO CURE,
SO VICTOR CREATED A UNIQUE
LIQUID NITROGEN FORMULA
TO SUPPLY HER CRYOCHAMBER
THAT KEPT HER IN STASIS
UNTIL A CURE
COULD BE FOUND.
AND HE DIED
BEFORE IT HAPPENED.
WELL, EVENTUALLY,
HER CRYOCHAMBER RAN OUT
OF VICTOR'S
LIQUID NITROGEN COCKTAIL,
SO WHEN SHE THAWED,
NORA LEARNED
THAT DOCTORS FOUND
A CURE FOR MacGREGOR'S,
SO THEY ADMINISTERED IT,
BUT SHE WAS SO DISORIENTED
BY THE 20-YEAR TIME GAP
THAT OFFICIALS
SENT HER TO ARKHAM.
SHE ESCAPED IN A BREAKOUT
3 YEARS AGO
AND HAS BEEN MIA
EVER SINCE.
-SO WHAT'S THE CONNECTION?
-DEE SMITHY IS
NORA FRIES' SISTER.
SEND ME THE ADDRESS.
I'LL FIRE UP
THE BATMOBILE.
OK.
UH, WHO'S BOUNCING
A BASKETBALL
OFF OF BRUCE WAYNE'S
SHELF OF FIRST EDITIONS?
THAT WOULD BE...
MY BROTHER.
OOH. THE GIRL'S
GOT REFLEXES.
YOU PLAY?
YEAH. IN ALL MY SPARE TIME.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
FREE FOR A DRINK
LATER?
JADA DIDN'T TELL YOU
ABOUT ME?
TELL ME WHAT, WILDER?
SHE MADE IT VERY CLEAR
SHE WANTED
NOTHING TO DO
WITH WAYNE ENTERPRISES
AND THAT I HAVE NOTHING
TO DO WITH HER.
OOH! YOU RUFFLED
SOME FEATHERS.
WHAT'D YOU DO?
BECAUSE NORMALLY,
SHE EATS THAT RAGS
TO RICHES STUFF UP.
REMINDS HER OF HERSELF.
SO YOU THINK YOU
KNOW MY STORY?
27, RAISED IN THE SYSTEM,
STINT AT BLACKGATE,
AND NOW...ACTING CEO
OF WAYNE.
OH, AND, UH,
YOU'RE MY SISTER.
SHE TOLD YOU THAT?
SHE DIDN'T HAVE TO.
HOW DID YOU FIGURE
THIS OUT?
OH, NANNYIES TALK
LIKE MINE DID WHEN MOMS
DISAPPEARED
FOR 9 MONTHS STRAIGHT.
HEARD ABOUT IT
AS A KID YEARS LATER.
WHY HER AND MY OLD MAN
DIDN'T SPEAK
FOR A FULL SUMMER
AFTER THAT.
SO IT WAS AN AFFAIR.
THEN WE FAST FORWARD
27 YEARS,
HERE'S SOME BADASS CHICK
ONE YEAR YOUNGER THAN ME,
SHOWS UP AT THE COMPANY,
THROWS MY MOM OFF HER GAME,
AND HAS GOT HER SCHEDULING
ALL THESE SECRET MEETINGS
WHILE I'M SUPPOSED TO BE
OUT OF TOWN.
POOF! HERE YOU ARE,
THE SISTER I NEVER KNEW
I HAD.
I--I WOULD ASK YOU
FOR A HUG,
BUT YOU LOOK LIKE YOU
COULD KICK MY ASS, SO...
PRETTY SURE YOUR MOM
MIGHT BEAT ME TO IT.
OUR MOM.
I DON'T THINK
YOU SHOULD BE HERE.
BUT I ALREADY PICKED OUT
MY OFFICE NEXT TO YOURS.
-WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
-BECAUSE IT'S THE CORNER.
WAY BETTER VIEW.
I MEAN, I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHY YOU'RE IN THIS PLACE.
IT'S SO...LIMITED.
YOU WANT TO PARTNER
WITH WAYNE ENTERPRISES?
MOM THINKS THAT I'M
IN THIS
JUST FOR THE PJs
AND FREE CONCERT TICKETS,
WHICH WOULD MEAN I'D BE
AN HONORARY VP
UNTIL SHE'S DEAD
IN HER LOUBIES
UNLESS I MAKE MY MARK,
SHOW HER WHAT I CAN DO.
SAME WITH YOU.
WHY DON'T YOU SHOW HER
WHAT SHE MISSED OUT ON
THE LAST 30 YEARS?
WHAT DO YOU SAY, SIS?
WANT TO JOIN FORCES,
SHOW HER WHAT WE GOT?
LUKE: YOU SAID YOU'D
THINK ABOUT IT?
RYAN: I COULDN'T
EXACTLY ASK HIM TO
WAIT IN THE LOBBY
WHILE I FOLLOWED THE 20
ON A MISSING FREEZE TANK.
WHAT EXACTLY IS THERE
TO THINK ABOUT?
WHAT IT MIGHT BE LIKE
TO ACTUALLY HAVE A BROTHER.
OK. I GET THAT,
BUT JADA JET
DIDN'T EARN HER SPOT
ON THE "FORBES" 150
BY MAKING IDLE THREATS.
SHE LITERALLY PROMISED
TO DESTROY WAYNE ENTERPRISES.
OK, OK.
I'M IN DEE'S HOUSE.
WE'RE LATE TO THE PARTY.
SOMEONE WAS HERE,
AND IT GOT UGLY.
NO SIGN OF DEE
OR THE FREEZE TANK
OR THE ROOMMATE
WE DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT.
I THINK NORA'S
LIVING HERE.
WAIT. I THOUGHT YOU SAID
THEY FOUND THE CURE
FOR MacGREGOR'S SYNDROME.
THEY DID. ACCORDING
TO NORA'S MEDICAL RECORDS,
SHE RECEIVED IT
YEARS AGO.
OK. WELL,
FROM THE LOOKS OF IT,
SHE'S STILL SICK.
MAYBE IT DIDN'T TAKE.
MAYBE DEE WANTED TO
PUT NORA BACK
IN HER CRYOCHAMBER TO
SAVE HER SISTER'S LIFE.
SO WHO BROKE
INTO THE HOUSE?
SOMEONE AFTER
THE SAME THING?
I DON'T SUPPOSE YOU
KNOW WHERE ONE WOULD
FIND A CRYOCHAMBER.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT ACE CHEMICALS?
ONLY THAT NO GOOD THING
EVER HAPPENED THERE.
AND I'M SENDING YOU
THE ADDRESS NOW.
HERE. EVERYTHING
YOU NEED TO KNOW
ABOUT CRYOGENICS.
MY BROTHER-IN-LAW
KEPT METICULOUS NOTES.
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
NORA: JUST LEARNED MY SISTER
WAS GONNA PUT ME ON ICE,
AND NOW I GOT A GUN
ON MY BAD HIP.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
I'M GONNA DO, RUN?
THESE ARE THE MUSINGS
OF A MADMAN.
I CAN'T READ THIS.
YOU GOT TO SHOW ME
HOW IT WORKS.
HOW ON EARTH WOULD WE KNOW
THE FIRST THING ABOUT THAT?
THEY DIDN'T EVEN OFFER
SCIENCE TO WOMEN
WHEN I WAS
AT UNIVERSITY.
SHOW ME...
OR SHE DIES.
BP AND HEART RATE
TOTALLY NORMAL.
98.6.
GLUCOSE LEVELS ARE
AS AVERAGE AS THEY COME,
WHICH ARE ALL
COMMON SYMPTOMS
OF FAKING IT!
OHH!
YOU KNOW, WITH
CARE LIKE THIS,
IT'S AMAZING YOU
MANAGED TO SAVE
ANY LIVES.
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH YOU, ALICE,
AT LEAST NOT PHYSICALLY.
I'M SORRY. I THINK
MY DANGEROUSLY HIGH FEVER
IS INTERFERING
WITH WHATEVER YOU
ARE HINTING AT.
THE POSTCARDS
FROM DAD? HEH.
YOU KNOW, IT'S FUNNY.
I WAS ACTUALLY
KIND OF JEALOUS OF YOU
WHEN I THOUGHT
THAT HE WAS WRITING
TO YOU AND NOT ME,
AND THEN WHEN I FOUND OUT
THAT IT WAS JUST YOU
BEING TOTALLY DELUSIONAL,
IT HONESTLY WAS A RELIEF.
I'M SO GLAD
MY MADNESS HAS SOOTHED
YOUR DADDY ISSUES.
DOES THAT HAPPEN A LOT,
THOSE DELUSIONS?
-JUST THE ONCE.
-MM-HMM.
SO THIS WHOLE PERFORMATIVE
"I'M SICK"...
THING ISN'T, HMM,
I DON'T KNOW,
A CRY FOR HELP MAYBE?
I LEARNED
A LONG TIME AGO
THAT CRIES FOR HELP
DON'T WORK.
LOOK. I'M
AN OFFICIAL DOCTOR NOW,
SO IF YOU NEED
ACTUAL HELP,
I HAVE TO GIVE IT TO YOU.
SO...DO YOU?
I SEE WHAT'S
GOING ON HERE.
YOU COULDN'T HELP
BATBOY,
SO NOW YOU'RE
BURDENING ME
WITH YOUR
SAVIOR COMPLEX.
-BATBOY?
-YEAH. LUKE.
IT SAYS IN HIS FILES
HE'S HAVING SOME
UNFORTUNATE
PERFORMANCE ISSUES.
YOU WENT
THROUGH MY FILES?
OK. THAT CABINET
IS LOCKED.
I BROKE OUT
OF THE CROWS
WITH A FISHING LINE.
YOUR OFFICE WAREHOUSE
CABINET DIDN'T STAND
A CHANCE.
ANYWAY, IT'S YOUR FAULT
FOR TAKING FOREVER
TO SEE ME AND NOT
GIVING ME ANY MAGAZINES.
I ASSUME THAT BATWOMAN
KNOWS SHE'S WORKING
WITH AN EMOTIONAL
TICKING TIME BOMB.
BATWOMAN DOESN'T BREAK
INTO MY FILE CABINET
BECAUSE IT'S CALLED
DOCTOR-PATIENT CONFIDENTIALITY.
PERFECT. I'M NOT
A DOCTOR,
SO WHAT'S THE ISSUE?
HMM. NOW YOU'RE
IN THE MIDDLE.
THAT IS A DILEMMA.
DO YOU TELL BOSSY PANTS
BATWOMAN
THAT LUKE'S IGNORING
HIS PTSD SYMPTOMS,
OR DO YOU KEEP
LUKE'S SECRET
BECAUSE YOU LOVE HIM?
I DO NOT LOVE LUKE...
LIKE THAT.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
SURE, BUT A LITTLE
PIECE OF ADVICE.
I'D KEEP THAT
TO YOURSELF.
TELLING RYAN
WILL ONLY, UM,
FILL YOU
WITH RESENTMENT.
HOW DO YOU FIGURE?
BECAUSE SHE'LL
IGNORE YOU, MARY.
I'M SORRY. DO YOU
NOT SEE YOUR PLACE
ON THIS TEAM?
I'VE BEEN ON IT
FOR LESS THAN A MONTH,
AND IT'S ALREADY
GLARINGLY OBVIOUS.
THEY DON'T SEE YOU
UNLESS THEY NEED YOU
JUST LIKE DADDY
AND JUST LIKE KATE,
SO IF YOU WANT TO
GO ON LIKING THEM,
IT'S PROBABLY BEST
YOU KNOW YOUR PLACE.
WATCH YOUR 6. GOT A READ
ON SOME MAJOR FIREPOWER
IN THE SOUTH PARKING LOT.
I GOT EYES ON 3 MORE INSIDE.
LUKE: COPY THAT.
BE CAREFUL, BATWOMAN.
WOMAN: THIS IS GOING TO MAKE
MY CLIENT VERY HAPPY.
NORA: UNTIL HE REALIZES
IT DOESN'T WORK.
DEE: CAN IT, NORA.
DO YOU THINK WE'RE
WALKING OUT OF HERE?
HAVE YOU SEEN
THEIR FACES?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
IT DOESN'T WORK?
DEE: IT WORKS FINE.
JUST A LITTLE DUST,
A FEW DISINFECTANT WIPES.
THE CHAMBER WORKS.
IT'LL FREEZE YOU SOLID,
BUT YOU DIE OF HYPOTHERMIA
EVENTUALLY.
WELL, THEN WHAT'S THE POINT
OF THIS STUFF?
CONSTANT EXPOSURE
TO THE FREEZE SERUM
WILL STOP TIME
AND KEEP YOU FROM AGING.
COMING OUT OF IT'S
A WHOLE OTHER STORY.
LOOK. MY HUSBAND
WAS BRILLIANT,
BUT HE DIDN'T REALIZE
THAT ONCE I WAS RELEASED
FROM THE CHAMBER
AND THAWED
TIME WOULD CATCH UP.
3 YEARS AGO, I CAME OUT
OF THAT THING A 34-YEAR-OLD,
AND LOOK AT ME NOW.
AT THIS RATE, I'LL BE
122 BY CHRISTMAS.
BUT YOUR SISTER'S ABOUT
TO LOCK YOU BACK INSIDE OF IT.
THE ONLY WAY TO STOP
MY SISTER FROM DYING
IS TO PUT HER BACK
ON HER ICE TILL
I CAN FIND A WAY
TO SLOW THE AGING.
THAT'S SOME DEDICATION.
WELL, IF WHAT SHE'S
SAYING IS TRUE,
THIS IS GOING TO BE
A MAJOR PROBLEM.
MAN: AGH!
ADD ME TO THAT LIST.
GET OUT OF HERE.
-CAN YOU WALK?
-BETTER THAN HER.
OK. THERE'S A CLINIC
ON RUCKA AND BENNETT.
IT'S NOT FAR. THEY'LL
TAKE CARE OF YOU.
-I CAN'T LEAVE DEE.
-I'LL FIND HER.
UNH!
A GUN? COULD YOU BE
MORE BASIC?
COME ON.
LET'S DO THIS.
RAAH!
COME ON!
WOMAN: HYAH!
ALL RIGHT. LET'S SEE
THIS THING IN ACTION.
UH-UH.
MY CLIENT WANTS TO KNOW
HOW IT WORKS
WITHOUT WASTING
THE PRODUCT.
BUT THAT'S THE WHOLE POINT
OF VICTOR'S LIQUID NITROGEN.
THE FORMULA IS WHAT
KEEPS HER ALIVE.
TURNING ON THE MACHINE
WITHOUT IT WILL JUST
BLAST HER WITH COLD AIR.
SHE'LL DIE
FROM HYPOTHERMIA.
DOES IT LOOK LIKE
I CARE?
I'M NOT KILLING BATWOMAN.
HOW LONG DO YOU
THINK IT'S GONNA TAKE
FOR MY DRIVER TO
FIND YOUR SISTER
JUST HOBBLING DOWN
RUCKA STREET
AND MAKE HER ROADKILL?
TURN IT ON,
OR YOUR SISTER DIES.
HMM.
IF BATWOMAN
DOESN'T DIE,
YOU DO.
TAKE HER TO THE CAR.
SHH.
BATWOMAN TO BATCAVE.
DEFINITELY NEED
A LITTLE HELP.
WHOA. TALK TO ME.
WHAT IS HAPPENING?
THEY TRAPPED ME
IN THE CRYOCHAMBER.
-WHAT?!
-GET ME THE HELL OUT OF HERE.
I'M PULLING UP
YOUR BIOMETRICS.
YOUR CORE
BODY TEMPERATURE'S
DROPPING LIKE CRAZY.
HEH. YEAH.
I'M PRETTY AWARE OF THAT.
OK, OK, OK.
ACCESS THE SUIT'S
TEMP REGULATOR.
YEAH.
OH, BOY.
SERIOUSLY, YOU COULDN'T
KEEP THAT TO YOURSELF?
THE REGULATOR
MUST HAVE FROZEN UP.
YOU HAVE 10 MINUTES
BEFORE FULL-BLOW
HYPOTHERMIA.
YOU NEED TO STAY
AWAKE, OK?
LUKE...
YOU NEED TO SUIT UP.
HELP DEE.
THEY TOOK HER SOMEWHERE.
WHAT? NO. I GOT TO
KEEP YOU FROM PASSING OUT.
I AM OK. GO FIND HER.
IF YOU PASS OUT,
IT'S OVER, RYAN.
I WON'T. OK?
GO FIND HER.
I PROMISED...
I PROMISED NORA I WOULD
PROTECT HER SISTER.
PLEA--PLEASE DON'T LET ME
DIE A LIAR.
NORA: ANY WORD FROM DEE?
BATWOMAN'S ON IT.
SHE WON'T LET ANYTHING
HAPPEN TO YOUR SISTER.
HAVE YOU CONSIDERED
CATARACT SURGERY?
IT WOULD BE A BIT
LIKE CLEANING THE WINDOWS
ON THE HINDENBURG.
DR. HAMILTON, I WAS
34 FOR 2 DECADES.
I GOT OUT AND STARTED
AGING DOUBLE-TIME.
LIFE'S CATCHING UP
TO ME.
WHY STAND IN THE WAY?
THOUGHT THAT'S WHAT
YOU WANTED--
TO LITERALLY STAND
IN THE WAY OF TIME.
I HAVE AN IDEA!
LET'S TALK ABOUT WHAT I WANT.
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?
GET THESE NANOBOTS OUT
OF ME NOW!
YOU KNOW I CAN'T DO THAT
BECAUSE THAT'S THE ONLY
THING PREVENTING YOU
FROM ESCAPING GOTHAM
ENTIRELY.
OH. I WONDER WHY I'D
WANT THEM GONE.
GET THEM OUT!
BATWOMAN WOULD KILL ME.
AND I WILL KILL NORA.
DO YOU NOT UNDERSTAND
CAUSE AND EFFECT?
-HOW DO YOU HAVE AN MD?
-LET HER.
MARY: WHAT?
ALICE: WHAT?
I AM SO SICK
OF PEOPLE SACRIFICING
THEIR LIVES FOR ME--
MY HUSBAND, MY SISTER,
THE RESEARCH,
THE LOST YEARS,
THE DESPERATION.
FOR WHAT? SO I COULD BE
TRAPPED ALL OVER AGAIN?
SO YOU WANT ME TO
KILL YOU?
COULD YOU BE
A WORSE HOSTAGE?
UHH!
YOU.
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
I LITERALLY JUST
LET HER GO.
I WAS BEING NICE TO YOU.
NICE? YOU THINK
I WANT...NICE?
YOU THINK I WANT
THIS STUPID ARRANGEMENT
WITH BATWOMAN, WHO
I CAN'T EVEN STAND,
AND LITTLE
MISS JUDGY TWO-SHOES
BEING NICE?
HA HA HA!
HEH. HEH.
IT'S NO WONDER I'M
LOSING MY FREAKING MIND.
I AM...SO SORRY
ABOUT THAT.
UM...BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
SHE'S MY SISTER.
HEH. YOU CERTAINLY
FIGHT LIKE IT,
BUT I'VE GOT TO SAY
I UNDERSTAND HER.
YOU UNDERSTAND THE WOMAN WHO
JUST HAD YOU AT KNIFEPOINT?
I FOLLOW THE NEWS.
SHE'S BEEN TRAPPED
HER WHOLE LIFE,
AND NOW SHE WANTS
HER FREEDOM.
DOES YOUR SISTER KNOW
THAT THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT?
DEE'S WASTED TOO MANY
YEARS OF HER LIFE
TRYING TO FIX ME.
I LOVE HER TOO MUCH
TO TELL HER THE TRUTH.
SOPHIE, ON COMMS:
BATCAVE TO BATWOMAN.
RYAN: SOPHIE.
AHH. BATWING'S EN ROUTE.
ARE YOU GOOD?
I'M FADING.
I JUST WANT TO SLEEP.
YEAH. THAT'S
THE HYPOTHERMIA TALKING.
YEAH. WELL, IT'S
AWFULLY CONVINCING.
YEAH, BUT YOU CAN
BEAT IT,
BUT YOU GOT TO
STAY AWAKE.
IF YOU SLEEP,
YOU DIE.
OHH. I CAN'T...
I CAN'T STAY AWAKE.
THEN MAYBE THIS IS
A GOOD TIME TO TELL YOU
I'M MAD AT YOU.
ME?
WHAT DID I DO?
WHERE DO WE STAND?
YOU AND ME?
BECAUSE YOU WERE
WILLING TO HAVE ME DO
ALL THE DIRTY WORK
TO FIND YOUR MOM,
BUT WHEN IT CAME
TO SHARING HOW YOU
ACTUALLY FELT ABOUT HER,
YOU WENT STRAIGHT
TO THE BATTEAM.
HANG ON.
YOU'RE TELLING ME...
THAT I HURT
YOUR FEELINGS?
I'M TELLING YOU
YOU DON'T KNOW ME
AT ALL.
YOU THINK YOU DO,
BUT YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
OK. HEH.
CAPTIVE AUDIENCE HERE.
WHAT SHOULD I--
WHAT SHOULD I KNOW ABOUT?
BATWOMAN, DON'T
FALL ASLEEP ON ME.
BATWOMAN! RYAN!
RYAN, WAKE UP!
WOMAN: RAAH!
HEY. HEY.
I GOT YOU.
YOU'RE OK.
SOPHIE: BATWOMAN,
ARE YOU GOOD?
BATWING!
SOMEONE TALK TO ME!
CHECK IN!
UH, YEAH. SHE'S OK.
SHE'S OK. SHE'S CONSCIOUS.
I GOT HER.
SOPHIE, ON COMMS:
TRAFFIC CAMS FOUND US
TWO VEHICLES MATCHING
THE SUVs FROM ACE
NORTHBOUND ABOUT 6 MILES OUT.
GOT A GLIMPSE OF DEE
IN THE BACK.
SO SHE'S ALIVE.
THANK GOD.
-CLEVER.
-ME?
SOPHIE.
ME?
THE WAY YOU KEPT ME
FROM NODDING OFF
BACK THERE.
YOU'RE CLEVER,
WHICH MEANS
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THERE IS SOMETHING
I DIDN'T KNOW
ABOUT YOU.
I WILL TAKE THAT
AS A THANK YOU.
ARE YOU FLIRTING
WITH SOPHIE RIGHT NOW?
WHAT? NO.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I KNOW WHAT FLIRTING IS.
WHAT WAS THAT?
I AM NOT FLIRTING
WITH SOPHIE.
GUYS...COMMS...ON.
OW.
THEY JUST TURNED
ONTO THE TRICORNER BRIDGE.
GOT THEM.
HOLD THIS.
WE'RE GOOD!
WE LOST THEM!
SOPHIE: NOT TO STATE
THE OBVIOUS,
BUT YOU DO SEE THAT IMPOSSIBLE
GAP IN THE BRIDGE, CORRECT?
I NEED A COPY ON THE CHUNK
OF BRIDGE MISSING
AT YOUR 12 O'CLOCK.
CONTROL FREAK.
ADD THAT TO
YOUR LIST, TOO.
BATWOMAN, WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?
IT'S WORKING!
GUN IT NOW!
RYAN: WHOO OOH!
YEAH-EAH! WHOO!
THAT WAS BADASS.
YOU GOT TO ADMIT.
IT WAS INTERESTING.
INTERESTING?
WOMAN, YOU ARE
HARD TO PLEASE.
HURRY UP!
SHE'S GAINING!
GET OUT. GET OUT.
LET HER GO.
LET'S HOPE VICTOR
TOOK GOOD NOTES.
UGH!
UGH.
WHAT THE HELL IS
HAPPENING TO ME?
NOT MUCH LEFT,
BUT RENEE WAS WILLING
TO CROSS IT OFF HER LIST.
THANKS FOR HAVING
MY BACK BACK THERE.
GUESS IT'S SAFE TO SAY
YOU FIGURED OUT
THE GLITCHES
IN YOUR SUPERSUIT.
YOU COULD SAY THAT.
MARY: IT'S BECAUSE HE
DISABLED THE FAILSAFE.
HIS DAD DESIGNED THE SUIT TO
REACT TO LUKE'S PHYSIOLOGY.
A SURGE IN HEART RATE
SHUTS IT DOWN.
THAT SEEMS
COUNTERINTUITIVE.
IT'S BECAUSE HE'S NOT
SUPPOSED TO WEAR IT
UNTIL HE'S READY.
MARY, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
I SHOULDN'T HAVE CLEARED
YOU FOR FIELD DUTY.
I'M SORRY.
I PUT YOUR LIFE
AND THIS TEAM IN JEOPARDY.
YOU WANT TO WORRY
ABOUT THE TEAM?
WORRY ABOUT
THE PSYCHOPATH
WHO HELD NORA
AT KNIFEPOINT TODAY.
ALICE WAS HAVING
A TEMPER TANTRUM.
YOU WERE HAVING
A PHYSIOLOGICAL REACTION
TO STRESS.
LOOK. I'M THE TEAM DOCTOR.
I KNOW WHAT I'M
TALKING ABOUT.
I HEAR YOU, MARY,
AND THANK YOU,
BUT I WOULDN'T BE
STANDING HERE
IF BATWING HADN'T BEEN
WITH ME LAST NIGHT.
MARY: AND WHAT ABOUT
NEXT TIME?
THAT'S THE RISK
WE BOTH TAKE.
NO OFFENSE, RYAN,
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE PTSD
FROM BEING SHOT.
LUKE: I DON'T HAVE
PTSD.
OK. GIVE IT
TO ME STRAIGHT.
ARE YOU UP FOR THIS?
ABSOLUTELY.
OK. THEN KEEP
AN EYE ON IT,
BUT UNTIL WE GET
THESE WEAPONS OFF THE STREET,
I NEED LUKE BY MY SIDE.
I HAD TO SAY SOMETHING.
NO, YOU DIDN'T.
THANK YOU.
YOU DON'T SLEEP,
DO YOU?
HE KNOWS I'M
HIS SISTER.
-HOW?
-HE'S SMART AND AMBITIOUS
AND INCREDIBLY RECKLESS.
HE WANTS TO WORK TOGETHER
BEHIND JADA'S BACK.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
IT'S FUNNY.
WHEN IT CAME TO FAMILY,
I NEVER ALLOWED MYSELF
TO ASK THAT QUESTION,
BUT THEN ALICE
RIPPED OFF THE BAND-AID.
UM...
IF I'M BEING REAL...
I WANT A MOM WHO KNOWS
ALL MY FOOD ALLERGIES
AND TELLS ME
MY SKIRT'S TOO SHORT
AND TEXTS MY GIRLFRIEND
ABOUT TV SHOWS THEY LIKE
AND LOVES ME...
UNCONDITIONALLY.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
I WANT A MOM.
IT'S HER LOSS, RYAN.
YEAH. WELL, JADA IS
ONE OF THE MOST
CONNECTED PEOPLE
IN GOTHAM,
WHICH MEANS MAKING HER
MY ENEMY
PUTS EVERY ONE I CARE
ABOUT AT RISK.
SO AS TEMPTING AS IT IS
TO HAVE A BROTHER...
I GOT TO PUT
THE TEAM FIRST.
MARY: THERE'S
A BRONCHODILATOR TO HELP
WITH THE BREATHING
AND MEDS TO HELP
WITH THE PAIN.
IT SHOULD BE ENOUGH
TO MANAGE THE PAIN
THESE NEXT FEW DAYS.
ARE YOU SURE YOU
WANT TO RISK BEING OUT?
GCPD's PROBABLY OUT
HUNTING FOR US AS WE SPEAK.
BATWOMAN TOOK CARE OF IT.
NEITHER ONE OF YOU HAVE
ANYTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
THANK YOU,
DR. HAMILTON.
VICTOR AND I HAD
OUR FIRST DATE IN THIS PARK.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE NOT TIRED?
WE CAN GO HOME.
DEE, I WANT TO BREATHE
IN THE FRESH AIR
WITH WHATEVER LUNGS
I HAVE LEFT,
AND THEN I WANT TO LET
IT ALL GO.
YOU'RE GIVING UP?
I'VE BEEN DYING
MY WHOLE LIFE, DEE.
INSTEAD OF TRYING
TO STOP TIME,
THIS ONCE, WHAT DO YOU
SAY WE ENJOY
THE PRECIOUS MOMENTS
WE HAVE LEFT?
OHH! AAH!
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD!