She's not here.
Stay sharp, Montoya.
Pamela Isley! Show yourself!
Surrender or we will use force.
I'm right here.
Stop.
Please.
Please don't make me do this.
Take the shot, Montoya.
No!
No, no, no!
Why are you doing this?
Because someone has to care.
Very few people can pull off green
with any swagger
but I actually don't hate this for you.
Yeah. It's interesting. I...
I'm sorry, I've never been
in a position before
where I couldn't be honest
because I was worried about hurting
someone's feelings so I'm stalling.
I think that's the sweetest thing
you've ever said to me.
- Did you order more food?
- No.
Did you order more strippers?
Ms. Hamilton, it's time to ask you
to pack your things
and part ways with us.
Rude.
You've racked up an $8,000 bill
without showing any ability
to pay for it.
I told the lady at the desk
ten times to try all my other cards.
They've all been declined,
Ms. Hamilton.
Oh, actually it's Dr Hamilton,
it's not a Miss.
I'm afraid I need to ask you
to leave
or the Metropolis PD
will be escorting you out.
This is all a misunderstanding.
Give me some time to figure it out?
Please, take all the time you need.
We'll accept your apology
and a complimentary bottle of Dom
for the inconvenience.
You're very kind, ma'am.
I know.
Did the bat bitches cut me off?
All your fancy degrees,
and you didn't see that coming?
I thought we were past this.
I mean, one would think
that nearly vine-squeezing
the life out of your bestie
and then crushing the only cure
for you in existence
was a pretty good indicator
that it was time to move on
from the friendship.
Anyone else find it ironic
that when I beg Ryan and Luke
for their attention
they're too busy with their own drama
but then when I finally step away
for some much-needed me-time
Mary Hamilton's the coveted
Bat Mission of the week?
If this is a lecture on
being Batwoman's most wanted
trust me, I already took the exam.
Well, what do I do?
You kill them immediately.
Alice.
Fine.
As someone who had
a so-called family member
obsessed with the idea
that I could change
here's what you do.
You make your friends
hate you so much
that they want to give up on you.
Flowers aren't a fix-all, Pam.
My partner lost a kidney.
But they're white tulips.
Technically
from the Liliaceae family.
They symbolize forgiveness.
Would you rather it be a kidney?
- I'm trying here, Renee.
- He could've died.
He was going to shoot me.
Because I couldn't.
I'm supposed to have his back.
No, you're supposed to have my back.
Don't you see how unfair that is?
I took an oath to uphold the law
and you're out there breaking it
constantly for the sake of what?
Mother nature?
I know global warming,
water shortage, extinction of species
is an inconvenient thought for you
but, unfortunately, this reusable
coffee mug isn't the solution.
What is the solution then?
Quitting your job?
Ostracizing our friends?
Becoming so obsessed to the point
where I don't even recognize you?
Are you coming with me or not?
Not if you go
where I can't follow you.
Stay here.
Stay the quirky, brilliant scientist
who loves reading and baseball
that I fell in love with
- a decade ago.
- She's gone.
She's blossomed into someone
who can stand up for herself.
And more importantly,
for those things that can't.
I froze Mary's bank accounts.
I think.
Internet cut out ten times.
And now I have
the spinning wheel of death.
That's awesome.
Does asbestos have a smell?
Anyone smell that?
Dead rat in the wall.
Give it three days, it'll pass.
We don't have three days.
You saw her clinic.
Yeah, it's completely overrun
by plant life.
You don't find that symbolic?
- We won't let her forget who she is.
- I hope.
That's sweet.
How's that working out for you?
I'm sorry, I left my sarcasm meter
in the Batcave
I no longer have access to.
Is there something you would like
to say to me?
- Take off the kid gloves, Ryan.
- Kid gloves?
You wouldn't have Marquis arrested
because he's family.
You underestimated Mary
because she's your friend.
And now you're locked out
of your Batcave
and your bestie's on the lam
with a serial killer.
You jump in if I'm missing anything.
Okay. What the hell
was I supposed to do?
Pummel Mary with batarangs?
Let them throw Marquis in Arkham
for a brain injury
that isn't his fault?
It's called making hard choices.
Why are we even here?
There wasn't a toxic sewer
with Wi-Fi access?
Renee's not wrong, Ryan.
We need a harder stance.
By agreeing with the woman
who's blackmailing me
because you're sleeping with her?
Wow, I think I smell the asbestos.
Maybe we should go get some air.
Look, I get it. Mary's your friend.
I thought I could plead and hope
and rationalize with Pam, too.
It didn't work.
Eventually, it got to the point
where she made me choose.
My obligation to the city or her.
So, what did you do?
Something Pam
would never forgive me for.
I sold my soul to Batman.
He knew he couldn't trust Arkham
to contain her
so he developed a desiccation serum
that mimicked the process
a plant goes through
when it's denied water and sunlight.
The device used to inject it
is coded to the serum
meaning it's also the only way
to extract it from her.
So if we got more of the serum,
we can use it on Mary.
I have the device but he only made
one dose of serum.
It's currently pumping
through Pamela's bloodstream.
So, where is she?
- No one knows.
- Okay.
But if we find her, then presumably
we could siphon the serum
and use it to stop Mary, right?
Wrong.
First of all, accidentally unleashing
an eco-terrorist
will not be a good look for us.
Second, do you know
what desiccation means?
We would be dehydrating Mary
to the brink of death.
No, the serum
was just to put Pam down.
And that was ten years ago.
If we remove it,
my guess is she stays dormant.
Unless she comes into contact
with sunlight or water.
As for point number two,
kid gloves, Ryan.
Did you hear what Renee just said?
Pam will never forgive her
for what she did to her.
We are not putting Mary
through that same torture
so she can hate us too.
This could be our only chance
to save Mary.
The true Mary would want us
to stop her
before she can do something
that she can't take back.
We cannot help her
unless we stop her.
Fine.
If I were Batman,
where would I stash Poison Ivy?
My best bet is that Bruce wrote about
Pamela Isley in his journals
which are in the Batcave here.
But Marquis' state-of-the-art
interior and exterior cameras
mean no root, balcony,
or garage access.
Can you hack into the feed
and buy me some time?
- Not with dial-up.
- Manpower?
Five security guards per floor.
- Digital upgrades?
- According to our former staff
every executive elevator
requires a thumb scan
and his office is locked
with a retinal scan.
Guys, we're not getting
into this building.
Why is Marquis calling me?
Am I supposed to take this?
What the hell does he want?
Guess I'm about to find out.
I'm sorry,
I was a detective for eight years.
I'm just learning now
that Bruce Wayne was Batman?
What up, sis? Quick question for you.
Is this thing legit?
What do you think I can hawk it for?
Buck 50? Two?
What are you doing, Marquis?
I'm redecorating my office.
You do know you had a chess set,
right?
- You should be in jail.
- Oh, samesies, sis.
Remember when you had me kidnapped?
That's illegal.
You wanna call it sixes and move on?
You need help. You need a doctor.
It's not too late.
- Hold that thought.
- Sir.
The planner's upstairs
ready to take you
to the station for the party tonight.
And your mask is here for a fitting.
Two seconds.
Sorry about that.
You were calling me a mental case?
You wouldn't have called me
if a tiny part of you
wasn't reaching out for help.
Just like there's a tiny part of you
that loves me, right?
Else, you would have had my ass
thrown in Arkham.
And because you love me, you tried
to turn me into an ice cube.
Anyway,
I just wanted to say thank you.
The cold, the near-death of it all.
Gotta say, it awoke something in me
because I've never felt this alive.
Marquis Jet is coming for you,
Gotham!
You'll be hearing from me soon.
Wanna talk about it?
I think Marquis is throwing a party
at Wayne tonight.
And we're gonna crash it.
So we should run our identities. Go.
Hello, I'm Spencer Glad,
former Olympic athlete.
Rumored to be the next owner
of the Gotham Knights.
I'll hit you up for floor seats,
Spence.
The name's Cecilia Langley.
Heiress to a whiskey fortune
and world traveler.
Penelope Devereux, who for some
reason runs a board game empire?
Honestly, dream job.
Just gonna say it,
my girl sounds hot.
Also, how are we not gonna run
into these people tonight?
Yeah, I sent some emails.
They think they're uninvited.
And yes, she is.
I fitted your mask with ocular
mesh scanners from the Batsuit.
Be careful. Sophie, yours is from
the Dollar Store. Go nuts.
Okay, so we get in,
get past security
get to the Batcave,
find Bruce's journals
and find Pam.
Oh, and, Penelope, you're French.
Wait, what?
Eight of clubs? What's this about?
Hopefully, we'll be long gone
before it matters.
Who wants to play a game?
There's nothing worse in life
than a fake smile.
Couple days ago
I sat down at the table
of my brand new board room
surrounded by men and women
who were supposed to be my soldiers.
And they told me
that I wasn't the right man
- to lead Wayne Enterprises.
- Yeah, right.
- Oh, man. Oh, I'm so sorry.
- Hi. I'll take this for you.
But it was the way that they said it.
No crack or anything. That's crazy.
So condescending.
Like they were mad about it.
Like this.
So I fired their asses!
Each of you has proven
to be of savage mind.
That's who I want
at my Wayne Enterprises.
Jack of Hearts.
Do we just crash a deranged group
job interview?
I'm afraid so.
Hands on the table, Jack of Hearts.
True or false.
When we climb to the top, we got
to be willing to get a little crazy.
True.
How's this? Close enough?
No. We need a full retinal map
to fool the scanner.
You need to be a lot closer.
How am I supposed to do that
while he's playing game show host?
All I know is I switch the SIM card
on his assistant's tablet
and now I have full access
to tower security cams.
Okay. It's not a competition.
Yeah, sure thing.
But Sophie just got
Marquis' thumbprint
so kind of just waiting on you here.
Complete this sentence.
The sick among us deserve our...
Pity?
The answer we were looking for
was fear.
Tough luck. Who's next?
Come on. Don't be shy.
Look, I promise, this is
the opportunity of a lifetime.
Three of Diamonds.
Oui, c'est moi.
Miss Penelope Devereux, I presume?
Okay. Here we go.
The only Parisian on my guest list.
You created the game
Three Murders at the Bowery.
May I say, your work
is most thoughtfully deranged.
Merci.
Just... just a few more seconds.
True or false.
An artist always puts herself,
no matter how dark, into her work.
Oui.
Whenever we reveal our darkness
into the light
we are no longer scared.
Non.
Finish this sentence.
A mother's love is...
Scan complete. We're good to go.
Not my problem.
You know, if my therapist was here,
she'd say it's never a good idea
to hunt a desiccated body
while angry.
Just tell me why she wants to be here
all of a sudden.
It's not all of a sudden.
We're planning to spend
our entire lives together.
If Bruce mentioned anything about Pam
there's a good chance
I'll understand it.
Just because you wanna kiss
and make up with her
doesn't mean we're good.
I get why you're pissed.
But remember something.
Poison Ivy cost me
the love of my life.
I'm trying to help.
I'll take your help,
then I want my name.
Batwoman's name, out of your mouth.
We've pretty much cleaned up
everything on your list.
That's a fun way of saying
the Joker's Joy Buzzer
- is still unaccounted for.
- Okay, we need Alice to find it.
Wait. Alice was your job, right?
And you were hooking up with her
at her place
which I hope is nicer
than her office.
My place is rent-controlled.
Who cares if it's nice?
Really thought Wayne Tower
was tall enough
for us to get to handshakes, ladies.
All right. Hey. I thought I told you
to lock the door.
We're the cleaning ladies.
Sorry about the mess.
Can you face the other way?
We kind of got a hidden entry
situation going here.
Let's have some fun.
Guys, please tell me
you've figured out
where Poison Ivy's buried.
We just got to the journals.
Be quick about it
because Mary just got here.
Are you serious?
Mary came home?
Is she looking for us?
Just judging a book
by its cover here
but I think it's more likely that
she's looking for Freak Fertilizer.
Any sign of Alice with her?
Not yet, but I'll keep eyes out
on the security cams.
Don't let her leave this building.
Great, I mean, she's been
so cooperative lately
- I see no problems there.
- Okay, call if you need backup.
If Mary's here, it's for a reason.
And I can assure you
it's not to dance.
Let's just get through these.
Hey, I promise, I just want to talk.
Okay, or I'll just grab a number,
stay right here.
Mary Hamilton.
Well, well.
I should probably fire my publicist,
Mary Hamilton
because you should know
your friends no longer live here.
Well, I'm no PR rep
but if she's the one who came up
with your "deck of cards" theme
it's definitely something
you should consider.
I'm not feeling the vibes
you're putting out.
And that's a shame because you...
you looked like
you'd be a lot of fun.
Don't give up on me so fast,
Mr. C.E. bro.
You haven't even heard the reason
I came all this way to find you.
Dance?
Okay. Okay, okay, okay.
We don't have time for this.
New plan.
Bruce archived these chronologically,
so let's start there.
When was the first time you contacted
Batman for help?
It was early June 2011.
Okay.
Does any of this look familiar?
This.
This is the Gotham City Dam.
Bruce wouldn't have desiccated Pam
around that much water.
He didn't. He needed to stop her
from destroying it.
The Dam was her next target.
Okay, okay. I'm sorry,
why did you love this woman?
Because through it all
I knew it really wasn't her.
What's happening to Mary,
what happened to Pam...
it wasn't a fair fight.
I appreciate the symbolism
but technically
you just killed a tulip.
You going somewhere?
Yes, I am.
Question is, do I pack
one toothbrush or two?
Guys at the precinct
mentioned something
about a break-in
at Gotham Dam last night.
You wouldn't know anything
about that, would you?
I haven't been studying my ass off
for my detective exam for nothing.
What are you planning to do there?
You want the truth
so you have to break up with me
or a lie so we can stay together?
Don't do that. Don't put this on me.
Why not?
You already know what I want.
I want to save Gotham
from becoming a toxic waste dump
and I'd like you
to support me while I do it.
So what do you want?
For you to choose one.
Your cause, flooding this city
wiping full neighborhoods
off the map.
Or me.
Above all else, I want you.
But I need you to trust
that I know what I'm doing here.
What is this for?
Forgiveness.
You think of something?
You're good?
You got something.
Bruce wrote that Poison Ivy
would have to be kept
where no one would look for her.
But somewhere he could get to her
- if he needed.
- So close.
He wouldn't have buried her
anywhere near their usual hotspots.
Docks, shipyards, back alleys...
No, it'd have to be dark and dry.
No water. No light.
No other plant life.
Water was his biggest concern.
A single drop could be enough
to re-animate her.
Gotham City is a damn island
where it rains 300 days a year.
Are you sure
he didn't make a deal with GCPD?
For some kind of special protective
custody?
She's not at Blackgate, and I checked
the "off-books" wing at Arkham too.
There has to be an answer
we're not seeing.
Oh, my God.
What if she's here?
You spend your whole life
in the service of logic
and forensic evidence
and then you know what love does?
It makes you want to say things
like, "I know she's down here.
I can feel her."
If she is in there, are you sure
you want to see her like this?
Ryan and I can handle it.
Thanks, but I owe it to her
not to run away and hide.
This has the schematics
for the tunnel system
below the Batcave.
I have no idea
where we're going to end up
so make sure we find our way back.
How far down does this go?
Even closer to hell than your office.
Okay, I need total quiet.
Sorry, guys.
Damn fraud alert on my credit card...
Silencing.
I think I got something.
Trying to isolate it.
Okay, I'm locked in.
I can hear it clear enough
to track the source.
- Hear what?
- Pam's heartbeat.
- Oh, my god.
- You have the device?
- Yeah, I...
- Then we need to move.
Whatever Mary's up to
she doesn't stay
in one place for long.
Luke, we think Pam's somewhere
in the lower tunnels.
That is actually brilliant.
But a lot of solid rock down there.
So we might lose contact.
Keep Mary there. Help is on the way.
Let's go.
So I keep wondering two things,
why are you here?
And where's Wilder?
You're seriously thinking
about your sister right now?
So you expect me to think
that I could steal her company
and she's just cool with it?
It's honestly kind of annoying
how much clinginess
runs in your family.
You want to know why Ryan
isn't paying attention to you?
It's because she's too obsessed
with "fixing" me.
You don't look broken to me.
Look...
Long story short, I just want
to move on with my life
with the one person left
who understands me.
But then I thought to myself
this Marquis guy
has a lot of weird baggage.
Maybe he wants to take revenge
on Ryan on my behalf?
What did you have in mind?
Well, look who stopped talking.
A little bonus for you.
It might help open up some doors
for you in the future.
Ryan, are we hot or cold?
Tell me we're scalding because
we're almost at the end of the map.
Well, it's getting louder,
I just don't know how much further.
To Batwoman, Mary and Marquis...
Luke? Luke? You copy?
Damn.
Okay, there's something's going on
with Mary upstairs.
- We're almost out of time.
- Guys.
Tell me she had
a charming personality.
That's the desiccation.
The serum leeches water
from the cells
includes skin and tissue.
And you wanna do this to Mary?
I'm trying
to prevent a poison ivy outbreak
from wiping out Gotham's
best and brightest upstairs.
Look, Ryan, I was you once.
I wanted to believe
that there was some magical solution
where I save the love of my life
without her hating me forever.
There isn't.
Mary is at the party.
The serum is here.
It's time to step up.
All right. Got it.
Hey, Luke, if you can hear me,
I'm headed up.
We're coming with you.
Stay and make sure
Pam doesn't wake up.
I'll check in once Mary's down.
Remember, no water breaks
and if you so much as have to sneeze,
don't.
Just in case.
Batwoman, if you copy,
I lost eyes on Mary.
Where are you?
- Didn't know you were coming.
- Get the hell off me, man.
I don't think
you should be talking like that.
You're not wearing the right costume.
What are you talking about?
See, I just wonder where you keep it.
Does it plug into
like a Tesla charger?
I don't have time for this.
Well, I think you do, Batwing.
She'd forgive you.
You have no clue
how much of a fighter she was.
I'm talking about Pam.
The woman you tell in love with.
Not Poison Ivy.
For the record, I take half the blame
for Alice going free.
Not the wisest move on my part.
We'll find her.
She'll screw up eventually.
Ping a traffic cam, rob a bank.
Alice?
More like hold-up a doughnut shop.
Oh, my God.
The fraud alert.
Whoever stole my card
they purchased
a three-tier strawberry cheesecake
and a grape soda,
then had it sent to her hotel room.
And you think it was Alice?
Knowing her,
she won't be there much longer.
I need to get her back.
Are you good here?
Doesn't look like she's re-animating.
I'll be fine.
Be careful.
Sorry, ma'am.
Elevators are temporarily down.
All of them? Why?
Just some hiccup
with the building computer system.
We'll get you on your way shortly.
Oh, Ryan, when will you give up?
The stairs are better for my calves
anyway.
Took you long enough.
Cake?
I believe you'll get 5% cashback.
You lured me here?
Lured you?
Let's not get kinky.
Alice, what the hell is this?
I made a juicy discovery.
And I've been dying to tell you
but you've been so hard to get alone
lately.
Honestly, I don't know
what's happened to our friendship.
We don't have one, for starters.
Besides the point.
You have been so kind
to house me on that prison cot
you call a pull-out couch
I just wanted to return the favor.
Your little lover
has been playing us.
- Renee?
- Sure.
Or whatever you call her
under the sheets.
Since when do you do me favors?
Because Re-nay-nay is a liar.
And she needs to pay
for being a bad one.
Says the world's biggest liar.
You know, Renee's huge mistake
was leaving me alone in her office.
Did she not think
I would snoop every nook and cranny?
Left cabinet. Second drawer down.
See for yourself.
I don't want to hurt you, Mary.
There's another promise broken.
What's in that?
Do you even know?
Batman made it to stop Poison Ivy.
When? A decade ago?
Do you even know the half-life
of its chemical compound?
You don't even know
what that will do to me, do you?
You gave me no choice.
Batwoman, hold up,
you ready for me to blow your mind?
How about we kill your two
little sidekicks at the same time?
A little brother-sister
bonding action?
Come on.
It was me.
I told him.
So you don't have to put yourself
on the "I don't know
what you're talking about" phase.
Mary, how could you?
You gave me no choice.
I always wondered
why I was the kid that got chosen
on that bus that day.
Couple dozen kids,
so why was I the one who got buzzed?
Everyone says the world's gone mad,
but I get it.
Batman had the Joker.
And Batwoman, you got me.
True or false, sis.
You gotta trust destiny.
False.
We make our own destinies.
You wish.
I've been in the bathroom
trying to finagle my way
out of Sophie's handcuffs
and you've been in here
drinking all the Dom?
Ryan had me beat.
She was about to inject me
with something.
And then she hesitated.
Whatever she was about to do to me
scared her.
Don't tell me you're getting
the conscience tingles.
Before I even knew
what was happening
she used the syringe on Marquis.
I don't know if it was to save Luke
or to protect her secret.
But...
all I know is, in that moment...
I was the least of her problems.
She still underestimates you.
I know it's silly...
but a part of me just wanted her
to see me as powerful.
Do you know those
loony tune delusions I was having?
Postcards from Dad,
imaginary friends
walking in on Sophie in the shower?
That last one happened.
Anyway, since your whole
Poison Mary metamorphosis
I have yet to have
a single delusional thought.
Which means babysitting you, my dear,
has made me less of a crazy person.
And if that's not powerful,
I don't know what is.
I know you can't hear me.
I know you hate me.
But I am sorry.
I've been sorry every day
I wake up to a badge and not to you.
Oh, my God.
Pam?
Pam, can you hear me?
Pam.
Oh, my God.
Desiccation is not pretty.
Do you think we should hook him
up to fluids?
Unless you want him to wake up.
He knows who we are.
The second he wakes up,
the whole world will too.
Yeah.
That's a big fat "if he wakes up."
Your call has been forwarded
to an automatic voice message system.
Jada Jet. This is Batwoman.
I have your son.
If you're looking for a way
to fix his brain
I suggest you find it quick.
Sophie?
How do you have reception
in the tunnels?
I'm not in the tunnels.
But you need to get there ASAP.
Sophie, where's Renee?
You know why you and Alice
haven't been able to cross
the joy buzzer off her list?
Renee has had it this entire time.
What do you mean she had it?
I mean she was never
going to let Alice free.
She lied, Ryan.
To Alice, to you, to me.
She was holding it over your heads
until one of you
found what she wanted.
Her soulmate.
Pamela Isley.