WOMAN ON OH, NO!
STOP!
THIS IS TERRIFYING.
THEY RELEASED THIS
TO THE PUBLIC?
KEEP YOUR NASTY FEET
ON YOUR SIDE
OF THE COUCH.
FINE. JEEZ.
CALL YOURSELF A ROOMMATE.
NO, I DON'T.
I'M A MILITARY-TRAINED
BABYSITTER
WHO MAKES SURE YOU'RE
RECEIVING YOUR PROPER MEDS.
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
SOMEONE'S ON THE BALCONY.
YOU DRANK MY PINOT?
I WAS SAVING THAT.
I'M SORRY. IT DIDN'T
HAVE YOUR NAME ON IT.
IT'S MY DAMN HOUSE.
ASSUME EVERYTHING
- HAS MY NAME ON IT.
- SHH!
DO YOU WANT THE
PSYCHOTIC SLASHER
OUT THERE TO HEAR US?
GO.
ON 3.
1... 2, 3.
- UGH.
- AHH.
THE DOOR WAS LOCKED.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I'M HERE FOR HER. GET DRESSED.
OH. ACTUALLY, I'M
SUPERCOMFY HERE
IN SOPHIE'S EX-HUSBAND'S
REALLY COOL SPORTS TEE.
RENEE INTERCEPTED SOME 911 CALL
WITH A LEAD
ON A POSSIBLE ROGUE WEAPON.
GET YOUR ASS DRESSED.
WELL, THIS CERTAINLY MAKES
SNUGGLING WITH SOPHIE SEEM TAME.
CAN YOU HAVE A LITTLE RESPECT
AND HELP ME GET HIM DOWN?
WHY ARE WE RUSHING? I'M
PRETTY SURE HE'S DEAD ALREADY.
YEAH. WELL, IT'S ONLY
A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE GCPD SHOWS UP
AND TAKES OUR EVIDENCE.
OH. PLEASE TELL ME WE DON'T
HAVE TO RECOVER HIS UNDIES.
JUST THE BINDINGS.
RENEE THINKS THE CULPRIT
USED CATWOMAN'S BULLWHIP.
AS IN ONE OF THE BAT TROPHIES?
WELL, THIS WAS EASY. FOUND IT.
CAN I PLEASE GO BACK
TO MY MOVIE NIGHT NOW?
I DON'T THINK THIS
IS CATWOMAN'S WHIP.
I DON'T CARE IF IT
BELONGED TO INDIANA JONES.
IF RENEE THINKS IT IS, LET HER,
SO SHE CAN CROSS
ANOTHER WEAPON OFF HER LIST
AND I CAN BE ONE STEP
CLOSER TO EARNING MY FREEDOM.
ACCORDING TO LUKE,
CATWOMAN AND BATMAN HAD A THING.
A THING? SO MUCH LEATHER.
HOW DID THAT WORK?
WELL FOR HER.
SHE APPARENTLY STOLE
SOME OF BATMAN'S NANOTECH
AND WOVE IT INTO HER WHIP,
MAKING IT INDESTRUCTIBLE.
THIS LOOKS LIKE IT WAS
CUT WITH A POCKET KNIFE.
I'LL HAVE SOMEONE FROM MARY'S
CLINIC PICK UP THE BODY
SO SHE CAN DO A THOROUGH EXAM.
YOU NEED TO FIGURE OUT
WHO KILLED THIS GUY.
AND YOU... PARTNER?
I HAVE DINNER PLANS.
RENEE LITERALLY HAS THESE
MISSIONS HANGING OVER OUR HEADS.
WHO COULD POSSIBLY BE
MORE IMPORTANT?
SOMEONE WHO HAS MUCH
MORE HANGING OVER MINE.
MY MOTHER.
NO, MRS. BAXTER. I DID
NOT USE YOUR INVESTMENTS
TO FUND A LUXURY MUSIC FESTIVAL.
WAYNE STOCK IS DOWN 53%,
AND OUR CRISIS MANAGEMENT
TEAM JUST QUIT.
AS CEO, I URGE YOU
PLEASE IGNORE THE TABLOIDS.
I TOLD YOU I WILL FIX THIS.
YEAH. OK. WHEN?
THE COMPANY'S IN THE RED
FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER,
AND YOU'VE BEEN ON NONSTOP
DAMAGE CONTROL
FOR THE LAST 3 DAYS.
WHAT IS THIS?
UH, ROOMIE, WHEN YOU
TOOK OUT THE TRASH THIS MORNING,
YOU CLEARLY FORGOT TO DUMP OUT
JADA'S DINNER PARTY INVITATION.
IT CAME BY COURIER YESTERDAY.
UGH. OF COURSE SHE TURNS
AN EASY E-MAIL
INTO A MASSIVE CARBON FOOTPRINT.
SHE JUST TANKED WAYNE.
WHY WOULD SHE EVER THINK
THAT YOU'D WANT TO GO?
GUESS WE'LL FIND OUT, WON'T WE?
YOU'RE GOING.
ALICE FOUND EVIDENCE LINKING
JETURIAN TO BLACK GLOVE.
ALICE, WHO IS LITERALLY
HALLUCINATING SO BADLY
THAT WE HAD TO PULL HER
OUT OF AN INSANE ASYLUM.
OK. LOOK. WE NEED
TO FIND SOMETHING
TO HANG OVER JADA'S HEAD
LIKE SHE HAS OVER MINE.
UNTIL THEN, SHE WILL
ALWAYS HAVE US AT HER MERCY.
WE NEED A SMOKING GUN,
SO WE BUG HER OFFICE
AND SEE WHAT WE FIND OUT.
SHE'S NOT INVITING
YOU OVER TOP SHOW YOU
HER SILK LINENS, RYAN.
SHE HAS AN AGENDA,
AND IF SHE WAS ABLE TO UNCOVER
WAYNE'S HIDDEN ACCOUNTS...
SORRY. WHAT WAS I SAYING?
"IF SHE WAS ABLE TO UNCOVER
WAYNE'S HIDDEN ACCOUNTS"...
EXACTLY. THEN WHO'S
TO SAY SHE CAN'T
UNCOVER YOUR
HIDDEN IDENTITY, TOO?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I NEED TO BE CAREFUL,
WHICH IS WHY I'M
BRINGING BACKUP.
SO YOU'RE RYAN'S DATE?
SO SAW THAT COMING.
IT'S NOT A DATE. IT'S RECON.
BUT YOU'RE WEARING
A PUSH-UP BRA,
SO IT'S A DATE.
YOU KNOW THIS IS
YOUR FAULT, RIGHT?
UGH. DON'T BLAME ME FOR
THIS REPULSIVE LOVE AFFAIR.
IF YOU'D NEVER TOLD RYAN THAT
HER BIOLOGICAL MOTHER
WAS STILL ALIVE,
WE WOULDN'T BE IN THIS MESS.
SOPH, THE GUILT I THINK
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE FEELING
IS SERIOUSLY KILLING
MY HALLUCINATION-FREE VIBES.
SERIOUSLY, FOR
THE LAST... 3 DAYS,
IT'S JUST BEEN ME,
MYSELF, AND I.
THE MEDS ARE WORKING.
CRAZY ALICE IS CRAZY NO MORE.
DON'T POKE THE BEAR.
TELL ME THAT YOU HEAR THAT.
IT'S YOUR PHONE. IT'S MONTOYA.
UGH. SERIOUSLY, PEOPLE.
I AM ON VACATION.
OH, NO. YOU'RE A CRIMINAL
WHO'S ON WORK RELEASE,
AND SHE SAID TO GET
YOUR ASS TO HER OFFICE NOW.
MAY I OFFER YOU A
BEVERAGE WHILE YOU WAIT?
THE MADAM RECOMMENDS
A 1994 COTE DES BLANCS.
- WE'RE GOOD.
- VERY WELL.
MADAM JET WILL BE DOWN SHORTLY.
"MADAM JET WILL BE
DOWN SHORTLY."
IS SHE FOR REAL?
AS REAL AS THE BLING
IN HER CHANDELIER.
I FEEL LIKE THE FOSTER KID
WHO ISN'T ALLOWED TO
SIT ON ANYTHING.
THAT'S THE POINT.
THIS IS AN INTIMIDATION MOVE
TO GET IN YOUR HEAD,
MAKE YOU THINK
YOU HAVE NOTHING AND
SHE'S GOT EVERYTHING.
THAT SHOULDN'T BE
TOO HARD CONSIDERING
MY LAST ADDRESS
WAS MY LICENSE PLATE.
RYAN, I'M GLAD YOU COULD COME.
AHH. I SEE YOU BROUGHT A FRIEND.
GIRLFRIEND ACTUALLY.
- SOPHIE. NICE TO MEET YOU.
- YOU, AS WELL.
SORRY TO INTERRUPT, MADAM.
THE CHEF ASSURES ME HE
HAS THINGS COVERED HERE.
GREAT. GOOD NIGHT, DAMIEN.
ON YOUR WAY OUT, WOULD
YOU PLEASE INFORM HIM
THAT WE'LL BE HAVING ANOTHER?
YES, MADAM.
- CHEF.
- HMM?
THE MADAM HAS
REQUESTED PREPARATIONS
FOR ANOTHER GUEST.
OH. THE MORE THE MERRIER.
THERE, THERE, LITTLE PIG.
UNH!
TIME FOR THE PROFESSOR
TO TEACH THE CLASS
HOW TO SQUEAL.
HA HA HA! HA HA HA!
SO HOW DID YOU TWO MEET?
RYAN AND THROUGH FRIENDS.
WAS IT A TUESDAY?
DEFINITELY BECAUSE IT WAS, UH...
TACO NIGHT.
AND... YOU OFFERED
TO BUY ME A DRINK
TO WASH DOWN THE CHIPS.
THE CHIPS. HEH.
UH, YOU KNOW...
YOU KNOW, WHEN THE CORNER
OF THE CHIP GETS STUCK
IN THE BACK OF YOUR THROAT.
YEAH. JUST THE COUGHING,
CHOKING, WATERY EYES.
I MEAN, I THINK THERE
WAS SWEAT INVOLVED.
- SOUNDS ROMANTIC.
- IT WASN'T CUTE,
BUT THAT'S THE POINT.
I MEAN... SOMEONE SEES YOU
AT YOUR NOT CUTEST
AND STILL ASKS YOU OUT?
I MEAN, AT THE END OF THE DAY,
WE JUST WANT SOMEONE
WHO'S LOYAL.
I KNOW THAT IF I WERE DYING
SOPHIE WOULD SIT BESIDE ME,
PUT HER ARMS AROUND ME,
AND TELL ME
EVERYTHING WOULD BE OK.
EXCUSE ME. BATHROOM?
LAST ROOM DOWN THE HALL.
WE SHOULD ALL BE SO LUCKY.
THAT WAS BEAUTIFUL.
HMM. YEAH.
NOW LET'S GET UGLY.
WHY AM I HERE?
IF THIS IS YOUR OLIVE BRANCH
FOR DESTROYING MY COMPANY,
YOU'RE GONNA NEED
A DAMN ORCHARD.
I COULDN'T HAVE BEEN MORE CLEAR
WHEN I TOLD YOU TO STAY
AWAY FROM MY FAMILY.
AND NOW I'M IN YOUR LIVING ROOM,
SO WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON?
WHATEVER'S GOING ON
BETWEEN YOU AND MARQUIS
NEEDS TO STOP.
WHO SAYS SOMETHING'S GOING ON?
A MOTHER ALWAYS KNOWS.
NOW I NEED YOU TO
ASK YOUR GIRL TO LEAVE
SO I CAN GET REAL WITH YOU.
GET REAL? RICH COMING
FROM THE WOMAN
WHO CONVINCED ME SHE WAS DEAD.
HMM. DYING WILL BE
THE EASY PART, RYAN,
FOR YOU AND A LOT OF FOLKS
IF YOU DON'T DO
EXACTLY WHAT I SAY.
YO! NOBODY AT THE DOOR?
WHERE'S MY MAN DAMIEN?
YOU NEVER KNOW
WHAT KIND OF PSYCHO
MIGHT COME WALTZING
INTO THIS PLACE.
MARQUIS, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
HEARD THERE WAS A FAMILY DINNER.
SOPHIE, BATCAVE.
COPY. ARE YOU IN?
10 BEDROOMS
AND 15 BATHROOMS LATER,
I FOUND HER STUDY.
OK. GOOD. FIND SOMEWHERE CENTRAL
AWAY FROM A.C. VENTS, SHREDDERS,
ANYTHING THAT CREATES NOISE.
ALL RIGHT. I'M AT HER DESK.
FIRE IT UP.
TESTING 1, 2, 3.
ALL RIGHT. WE ARE UP.
NOW GET OUT OF THERE.
I WILL IN TWO SECONDS.
SOPHIE, I STRONGLY SUGGEST
THAT YOU GET OUT OF THERE.
LOOKS LIKE RYAN WASN'T
THE ONLY ONE
CUT OUT OF THE FAMILY.
I'M GONNA SEND YOU A FACE
TO RUN THROUGH REC.
AH. GO FOR IT. STANDING BY.
SOPHIE?
LUKE, DO YOU COPY?
HEY. HEY, SOPHIE.
THE POWDER ROOM'S ON
THE FIRST FLOOR, HONEY.
BIG HOUSE. GOT LOST.
DINNER'S READY.
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO HAVE
A SECRET PARTNERSHIP,
AND YOU'RE SITTING THERE
HAVING SECRET DINNERS WITH HER?
WHOSE SIDE ARE YOU ON?
I HATE TO BREAK IT TO YOU.
SHE ALREADY KNOWS
ABOUT THE PARTNERSHIP.
HOW?
CAN WE PLEASE EAT
BEFORE ANY MORE GUESTS ARRIVE?
SO SHE DOESN'T THINK
IT'S A TROPHY.
OH, SOMETHING ABOUT BATMAN AND
CATWOMAN BETWEEN THE SHEETS.
PERSONALLY, I DIDN'T THINK
HEROES DID THAT SORT OF THING,
BUT, UH, WHAT DO I KNOW?
I'M A VILLAIN.
THEN PROVE ME WRONG.
OHH. THIS IS A RECORD
OF EVERY ROGUE
THAT'S TORMENTED GOTHAM.
IF IT'S NOT A CATWOMAN WANNABE,
THEN USE THAT
BEAUTIFULLY DEMENTED MIND
AND TELL ME WHO WOULD STRING UP
A NAKED MAN IN AN AUTO
SHOP WITH A BULLWHIP.
MAGPIE... NOT POSSIBLE. TOO MANY
SHINY PIERCINGS LEFT ON THE VICTIM.
SHELLY GAYNOR... AKA THE WHIP.
SOUNDS PROMISING.
MMM... NO. ANIMAL ADVOCATE.
HER WHIP WAS FAUX LEATHER.
HMM.
WELL, THIS ONE IS
KINKIER THAN A GARDEN HOSE,
BUT, UM, TALIA AL GHUL
IS FAR TOO IMPATIENT
FOR PERFORMATIVE VICTIM STAGING.
I THINK WE FOUND OUR GIRL...
MANIPULATIVE, OBSESSIVE,
BACKSTABBING.
WHO IS SHE?
YOU.
WHAT'S WITH YOUR CREEPY
OBSESSION WITH POISON IVY?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
MMM. HEH. YOUR CASE FILES
ON EVERYONE ELSE ARE... ANEMIC,
BUT THIS ONE ON PAM ISLEY READS
LIKE YOU'RE, UH, PLANNING
ON WRITING A BIOPIC...
JUICY INTERVIEWS,
DETAILED FACT SHEETS.
OHH! A CONFIDENTIAL
PSYCHOLOGICAL EVALUATION.
TSK, TSK, TSK, TSK.
NOW YOU NEED TO PROVE ME WRONG.
ARE BATWOMAN AND I LOOKING FOR
THESE WEAPONS OF MASS DESTRUCTION
TO STOP CRIMINALS?
BECAUSE I THINK THAT
YOU BROUGHT US TOGETHER
TO FIND ONE VINY VIXEN
IN PARTICULAR.
ANYBODY ELSE FEEL A LITTLE
SORRY FOR THAT THING?
ROASTED SUCKLING IS CONSIDERED
A DELICACY IN MOST OF THE WORLD.
I'M VEGAN, SO IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT CONTINENT MY ASS IS ON.
I'M NOT TOUCHING THAT.
PERHAPS MORE WINE
WILL ENHANCE THE EXPERIENCE.
OUR ESTEEMED CHEF FLEW
FROM METROPOLIS
TO COOK FOR US.
HE COMES HIGHLY RECOMMENDED.
SO IF I MAY,
YOU'RE THE ESTRANGED DAUGHTER
WHO JUST RECENTLY BONDED
WITH YOUR BROTHER,
BUT THAT'S BAD BECAUSE HE HAS
A CODEPENDENT RELATIONSHIP
WITH HIS MOTHER, WHO
NOW SEES YOU AS A THREAT
TO HER RELATIONSHIP
WITH HER SON.
ZOEY'S DISSERTATION IS ON
MODERN FAMILY DYNAMICS.
PARTICULARLY TRIANGULATION
AS IT RELATES
TO BOWEN'S FAMILY
THEORY PARADIGM...
RESCUER, VICTIM, PERSECUTOR.
THAT'S INTERESTING.
DOES BOWEN HAVE A TERM
FOR BACKSTABBING SISTERS?
UH, I NEED THE LADIES'.
TANNINS GO RIGHT THROUGH ME.
- BACKSTABBING SISTERS?
- MM-HMM.
I WASN'T THE ONE WHO
ORCHESTRATED THIS WHOLE DINNER.
JADA DID.
WAS THAT WHAT YOU WANTED?
MARQUIS FINDS OUT I'M
HAVING DINNER WITH HIS MOM,
SO HE STOPS TRUSTING ME.
IF WE'RE GOING TO
HAVE A CONVERSATION ABOUT TRUST,
LET'S TALK ABOUT
WHAT YOUR GIRLFRIEND THOUGHT
SHE WAS GOING TO FIND
IN MY STUDY.
EXACTLY. SO DON'T TALK TO ME
ABOUT HAVING AN AGENDA.
YOU'RE RIGHT, JADA. I DID
COME HERE WITH AN AGENDA.
I CAME TO SAY THANK YOU.
THANK YOU FOR GIVING ME UP.
THANK YOU FOR WALKING AWAY
AND LETTING ME BE
SOMEBODY ELSE'S PROBLEM
BECAUSE I DIDN'T GET THE BUTLERS
OR THE 5-COURSE MEAL
OR THE MANSION.
I GOT A HOME. I GOT LOVE.
I GOT A REAL MOTHER.
SHOULD HAVE KNOWN, ZOEY.
WINE AND FAMILY DRAMA
DO NOT MIX.
WHY CAN'T I FEEL ANYTHING?
TURN THE FAUCET, ZOEY.
AAH!
GOT TO SAY I'M NOT ABOUT TO LET
MY BABY SISTER WIN
BEST SPEECH OF THE NIGHT.
MARQUIS, HAVEN'T WE HAD ENOUGH
THEATRICS FOR ONE EVENING?
DON'T WORRY.
I'LL KEEP IT SIMPLE.
TO FAMILY AND LOYALTY.
- YOU OK?
- WHAT?
I CAN'T MOVE MY ARMS.
RELAX.
JUST A LITTLE PARALYTIC.
YOU MON...
OK. MAYBE A LOT OF PARALYTIC.
GET AWAY FROM US.
YOU'RE NOT AN EASY
WOMAN TO GET ALONE.
PRACTICALLY HAD TO CONVINCE YOU
I WAS ROYALTY TO GET
THE KEYS TO THE KINGDOM.
YOU DON'T REMEMBER ME, MRS. JET?
I HAVE NO IDEA WHO YOU ARE.
DO YOU REALLY FIRE
SO MANY PEOPLE
THEY'RE ALL A BLUR?
LAZLO VALENTIN. I WAS A CHEF
IN THE DINING HALL
AT YOUR OFFICE
UNTIL YOU FIRED ME.
VALENTIN. OK.
I REMEMBER THE NAME.
GOOD FOR YOU.
YOU KNOW WHAT I REMEMBER?
TELLING MY FAMILY,
"HEY, GUYS. NO MORE MONEY'S
COMING IN FOR A WHILE.
"BOSS LADY HATES
DADDY'S COOKING,
SO NOW NOBODY WANTS
TO HIRE HIM ANYMORE."
YEAH, AND I REMEMBER
THE DIVORCE PAPERS,
THE DEBT COLLECTORS,
THE REPO MAN.
DO YOU REALLY THINK
SHE REMEMBERS
THE DAMN COOK
FROM THE BUILDING CAF?
- MARQUIS.
- NAW. YOU PROBABLY SAID
THE FOOD SUCKED, YOUR
STAFF REPLACED HIS ASS.
IT'S JUST BUSINESS, BRO.
JUST BUSINESS?!
I LOST MY FAMILY BECAUSE OF HER,
SO NOW YOU'LL LOSE YOURS.
YOU TOLD MARQUIS
ABOUT THIS DINNER.
HOW ELSE COULD YOU WATCH ME
CHOP HIM INTO BACON BITS?
BUT THE UNEXPECTED
DAUGHTER... HA HA HA!
TALK ABOUT AN AMUSE-BOUCHE.
- HUH!
- AGH!
AAH! UGH!
MARQUIS, COME ON.
I CAN'T... I CAN'T MOVE.
ZOEY... SHE'S STILL UPSTAIRS.
I GOT HIM. GO.
I'LL FIND ZOEY.
GET OUTSIDE. CALL FOR HELP.
I GOT YOU. COME ON.
ZOEY. ZOEY, WE GOT TO GO.
AAH!
IT WON'T OPEN.
WHY WON'T IT OPEN?
HE MUST HAVE LOCKED US
IN FROM THE OUTSIDE.
MY PHONE HAS NO SERVICE.
MINE EITHER.
WHICH LITTLE PIGGY
WENT TO MARKET?
SHOULD HAVE STAYED HOME?
UPSTAIRS. FOLLOW ME.
GO. GO WITHOUT ME.
NO, MARQUIS. COME ON.
YOU CAN DO THIS. LET'S GO.
AHH! UNH!
AAH! UNH!
A LESSON FROM PROFESSOR PYG!
NOBODY LIKES AN UNINVITED GUEST!
HYAH! UNH!
UNH! OHH!
COME ON. COME ON!
ERRR!
HUH!
ERR! HA HA HA!
I'LL HUFF, AND I'LL PUFF
AND BURN YOUR HOUSE DOWN!
HE'S GONE... FOR NOW.
ZOEY'S DEAD.
OH, MY GOD.
AND HE'S NOT LEAVING THIS HOUSE
UNTIL WE ARE, TOO.
WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
IT'S A PANIC ROOM.
I CONVERTED ONE
OF MY CLOSETS A FEW YEARS BACK.
YOU MUST HAVE A LOT OF ENEMIES.
SECRET CLOSET SPACE AND ALL.
SIGNAL'S DEAD.
I HAD A CALL DROP EARLIER.
HE MUST HAVE ACTIVATED
SOME SORT OF...
SIGNAL BLOCKER.
TELL ME YOU HAVE A GUN IN HERE.
UH-UH. I DON'T BELIEVE IN GUNS.
WHAT'S WRONG?
NOT TORTUROUS ENOUGH?
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
EVERYBODY, JUST CHILL, OK?
SOMEONE WILL EVENTUALLY
REALIZE WE'RE MISSING
AND COME LOOKING FOR US.
WE JUST NEED TO HANG UNTIL THEN.
MARQUIS?
MARQUIS! MARQUIS! MARQUIS!
MARQUIS!
PAMELA AND I MET AT GOTHAM U.
I WAS STUDYING CRIMINAL LAW.
SHE WAS INTO BOTANY,
COMPLETE OPPOSITES,
BUT COULDN'T SEE A
FUTURE WITHOUT THE OTHER.
- LOVE THAT.
- AT THE SAME TIME,
ONE OF HER CLASSMATES
WAS CONDUCTING
THESE OBSESSIVE
EXPERIMENTS FOR HIS Ph.D.
HE AND PAM WERE COMPETITIVE,
BOTH SUPERSMART, KIND OF NERDY.
SHE THOUGHT IT WAS
HARMLESS UNTIL ONE NIGHT
HE ABDUCTED PAM AND USED
HER AS HIS GUINEA PIG.
LET ME GUESS...
THAT'D BE MARC LeGRAND.
WHATEVER HE INJECTED
HER WITH WAS POISON,
SOME AWFUL COMBINATION
OF THINGS AROUND HIS LAB...
OLEANDER, NIGHTSHADE,
WATER HEMLOCK.
CHANGED HER ENTIRE PHYSIOLOGY.
TURNED HER INTO
A GREEN-THUMBED PSYCHO.
SHE DIDN'T SEE IT THAT WAY.
SHE WANTED TO SAVE THE PLANET,
AND THAT MEANT PUNISHING
ANYONE DESTROYING IT.
EXCEPT AN UP-AND-COMING COP
SHACKING UP WITH A SERIAL KILLER
KIND OF PUTS A CRAMP
IN THE OLD CAREER TRAJECTORY.
SHE WENT FROM
COMPASSIONATE AND LOVING
TO RECKLESS AND IRRATIONAL
OVERNIGHT.
TOTAL PERSONALITY CHANGE.
IT EVENTUALLY JUST
TORE US APART.
SUBTEXT... YOU CHOSE
YOUR CAREER OVER YOUR GIRL.
SHE WAS LOST... OK?
GONE. EMOTIONALLY, MENTALLY
A SHELL OF THE PERSON I KNEW,
AND I... I WAS YOUNG.
I HAD NO IDEA HOW TO SAVE HER.
OH, RELAX. I'M NOT
ACTUALLY INVESTED
IN YOUR LOVE STORY.
SO WHERE'S POISON PAM?
THAT'S A QUESTION FOR BATMAN.
WELL, SHE'S NOT
IN ARKHAM... I WOULD KNOW...
AND BORING BATMAN DIDN'T
ACTUALLY KILL ANYONE,
SO UNLESS SHE SLITHERED
UP JACK'S BEANSTALK...
MY THEORY IS HE HID HER
UNDER THE CITY SOMEWHERE
AWAY FROM WATER AND SUNLIGHT
AND ANYONE SHE COULD HURT.
WHY WOULD BATMAN BURY
YOUR GIRLFRIEND ALIVE?
BECAUSE I TOLD HIM TO.
THIS SHOULDN'T BE HAPPENING.
WHAT SHOULDN'T HAPPEN?
THIS LONG, SAPPY TANGENT,
ESPECIALLY WHEN THERE'S A
POTENTIAL SADIST ON THE LOOSE.
I'M GOING TO GO SEE
OUR MEDICAL EXPERT
AND SEE IF SHE FOUND
ANYTHING ON THE VIC'S BODY.
DRINK THE WATER, MARQUIS.
WE'RE GONNA MAKE SURE SHE'S OK.
HE DRANK THE MOST,
SO IT'S HITTING HIM FIRST,
BUT IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE IT'S ALL OF US.
OK, OK.
65 OVER 30.
THAT'S BAD.
IF IT KEEPS DROPPING,
HE'S GONNA DIE.
- HE NEEDS ADRENALINE.
- I KNOW.
THERE'S NONE IN HERE.
THERE ARE EPIPENS.
MY HUSBAND CARRIED THEM
FOR HIS ALLERGIES.
- WHERE?
- WITH OUR CAMPING GEAR.
IN THE BASEMENT.
TELL ME THERE'S ANOTHER WAY
TO GET INTO THE BASEMENT.
WHAT THE HELL IS HE DOING?
BUILDING A BOMB.
I'M GONNA NEED YOUR HELP.
OHH.
COME ON.
LAZLO. LAZLO, WHERE ARE YOU?
LAZLO, I WANT A TRUCE.
YOU NEED MONEY? HOW MUCH?
I'LL GIVE YOU ANYTHING YOU WANT.
LET'S TALK.
LAZLO, I'M SORRY.
I REALLY AM.
RAH! OHH!
UNH!
AGH!
IT WASN'T PRETTY,
BUT SHE MADE IT.
SO ARE YOU REALLY
RYAN'S GIRLFRIEND,
OR WAS THAT A LIE, TOO?
WANT TO KNOW WHO I REALLY AM?
I'M JORDAN MOORE'S SISTER.
I'M SORRY. I'M LIGHTHEADED.
AM I SUPPOSED TO
KNOW WHO THAT IS?
YOUR MEN ABDUCTED HER
AND INJECTED HER
WITH FREEZE SERUM,
KILLED 3 OF HER FRIENDS,
NEARLY KILLED HER.
WHAT... WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
STOP!
DON'T TELL ME YOU DIDN'T KNOW
ABOUT HUMAN EXPERIMENTS
BEING CONDUCTED
BY YOUR OWN EMPLOYEES.
SO IS THAT WHAT YOU
WERE DOING IN MY STUDY,
LOOKING FOR EVIDENCE?
WHAT'D YOU FIND, SOPHIE,
"THE ANARCHIST COOKBOOK"?
LOOK. I AM SORRY ABOUT WHAT
HAPPENED TO YOUR SISTER,
BUT I HAD NOTHING
TO DO WITH THAT.
I'M NOT THE MONSTER
YOU'VE MADE ME OUT TO BE.
STAY WITH ME, SON. MAMA'S HERE.
OHH.
OF COURSE.
PROFESSOR COME ON!
OK. OK.
COME ON, RYAN. MOVE YOUR ARM.
MOVE YOUR DAMN... ARM!
UNH!
COME ON, COME ON.
COME... ON.
VIC HAD MOTORCYCLE GREASE
UNDERNEATH HIS FINGERNAILS.
I FOUND A SIMILAR
BUT NOT EXACT VISCOUS SYNTHETIC
ON THE BULLWHIP.
FASCINATING.
WHAT'S WITH
THE BOTANICAL GARDEN?
OH, DID THE MEDICAL BOARD
TAKE AWAY YOUR LICENSE
AND LEAVE YOU TO THE
WHIMS OF HERBAL MEDICINE.
DO YOU KNOW HOW I SAVED
JORDAN MOORE'S LIFE?
- NO.
- I MIMICKED THE ANTIFREEZE
SYNTHESIS DONE BY PLANTS
TO SURVIVE
SUBZERO TEMPERATURES.
YOU WANT TO KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE PLANTS ARE
SMARTER THAN HUMANS.
THEY'RE RESILIENT,
THEY'RE INTUITIVE,
THEY GIVE BACK MORE
THAN THEY TAKE.
GOT IT. JEEZ. SORRY I ASKED.
ANYWAY, DO YOU REMEMBER
WHEN YOU WERE BEING
ALL HERO COMPLEXY
AND TOLD ME BECAUSE
YOU'RE A OFFICIAL DOCTOR
NOW IT IS YOUR DUTY
TO HELP ME WHEN THE TIME COMES?
WELL... THAT TIME IS UPON US.
THE DELUSIONS ARE BACK.
BETWEEN THE... INMATES
IN ARKHAM,
THE EXPERIMENTAL MEDS, THE GENERAL
MISE EN SCEÈNE OF CAPTIVITY,
I ASSUMED IT WAS THE ASYLUM
THAT WAS MAKING ME CRAZY.
DON'T GET ME WRONG.
I HAVE ENJOYED
MY FAIR SHARE OF DISASSOCIATION.
YOU'RE TALKING TO THE
GIRL WHO CONVINCED HERSELF
THAT 12 YEARS
OF SEWING SKIN MASKS
WAS A FANCY TEA PARTY.
BUT I WAS IN CONTROL THEN.
THIS IS DIFFERENT.
I'M NOT IN CONTROL ANYMORE.
AS IF WHAT'S HAPPENING
ISN'T OBVIOUS?
YOU REAP WHAT YOU SOW, ALICE.
ALL OF THE MURDERS,
THE PAIN, THE MISERY
THAT YOU'VE INFLICTED, THEY
WERE THE SEEDS THAT YOU PLANTED
FOR THE GARDEN
YOU'LL BE BURIED IN.
GOT IT.
SPEAKING OF GARDENS,
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN FROLICKING?
GOTHAM PARK.
I THINK I EXPOSED MYSELF
TO WHATEVER THAT THING IS.
OHH. I TOOK A SAMPLE
OF THE VINE,
BUT I CAN'T FIGURE OUT
IF IT'S POISON OAK,
POISON SUMAC, POISON HEMLOCK.
POISON IVY.
LET ME IN!
OH, MY GOD.
HE'S GOT RYAN.
OPEN THIS DOOR RIGHT NOW!
BUT HE WANTS YOU.
IF I OPEN THIS DOOR,
I'M AS GOOD AS DEAD.
UGH.
YOUR LESSON IS
THAT WHEN SOMEONE SHOWS YOU
WHO THEY ARE BELIEVE THEM
BECAUSE IF I'M HOW SHE
TREATS THE PEOPLE
SPENDING THEIR DAYS
TRYING TO IMPRESS HER,
GUESS HOW SHE'LL TREAT
SOMEONE SHE SEES AS A THREAT.
GET AWAY FROM MY DAUGHTER!
TAKE ME INSTEAD.
SHE DID NOTHING TO YOU.
WELL, WELL, MADAM SWINE.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOUR LESSON IS?
PERFECTION COMES AT A PRICE.
ERR!
RRR!
RAAH!
- RAH!
- LOOK OUT!
INCOMING!
AAGH!
UNH!
AHH! AHH! AHH!
AAH!
AHH. FLAMINGO.
EXCUSE ME?
THE BULLWHIP KILLER.
IT'S THE FLAMBOYANT, PINK
HARLEY-STRADDLING PSYCHO FLAMINGO.
VICTIM WAS IN A RIVAL GANG,
DNA EVIDENCE,
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH... SCIENCE,
BUT THE POINT IS
IF THE BIKER BOOT FITS...
I'LL ALERT THE VICTIM'S
FAMILY AND PUT OUT
A WARRANT FOR THIS FLAMINGO,
AND I GUESS THAT MEANS CATWOMAN'S
WHIP IS STILL OUT THERE.
OHH, AND I CAN'T WAIT
TO GET TO THAT
WHEN I'M BACK FROM TAHITI
BECAUSE I BELIEVE THAT, UM...
THIS BUYS ME A WEEK'S VACATION.
AND WHAT IS THIS?
YOUR GIRLFRIEND,
ALTHOUGH SHE IS LOOKING
A LITTLE FRAIL.
THIS IS A DEAD CUTTING
FROM HER VINE.
- WHERE DID YOU GET THIS?
- DOES IT MATTER?
I REUNITED YOU
WITH YOUR LONG, LOST LOVE.
TO THINK I WAS CONFUSED
ABOUT BATMAN AND CATWOMAN.
IT MATTERS BECAUSE THESE
VINES DON'T DIE UNLESS...
UNLESS WHAT?
UNLESS SHE'S
INFECTED SOMEONE ELSE.
WHAT YOU THINKING ABOUT?
- WHAT WAS FOR DESSERT.
- HEH.
JADA'S HIDING SOMETHING.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT,
BUT I TRUST MY GUT ON THIS.
SHE'S LYING.
THEN IT'S TIME FOR HER
TO TELL ME EVERYTHING.
CALL YOU TOMORROW,
TELL YOU WHAT I LEARNED?
GOOD LUCK.
GREAT FIRST DATE, HUH?
DEFINITELY MEMORABLE.
AND PEOPLE WONDER WHY I
DON'T THROW DINNER PARTIES.
YOU OK?
YOUR GIRLFRIEND LEFT THIS.
ONCE A CROW ALWAYS A CROW, HUH?
I DIDN'T KNOW
ABOUT JORDAN MOORE.
YOUR WORD IS NOT GOOD
ENOUGH, JADA.
WELL, IT HAS TO BE.
I DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT JORDAN
OR THE EXPERIMENTS
OR THE DEATHS.
HOW COULD I? I'M A MOTHER.
THE WHOLE POINT OF ALL THIS
WAS THAT NO ONE ELSE GET HURT.
THE WHOLE POINT OF WHAT?
I'M GONNA TELL YOU SOMETHING,
AND FOR YOUR SAKE, FOR
EVERYONE YOU LOVE'S SAKE,
YOU NEED TO KEEP IT TO YOURSELF.
- YOU NEED TO PROMISE ME THAT.
- I CAN'T,
NOT UNTIL I KNOW WHAT IT IS.
MARQUIS IS SICK.
WHAT'S GOING ON, MARQUIS?
WHAT'D YOU GET
FOR YOUR BIRTHDAY?
A BUG COLLECTOR KIT.
HA! THAT'S COOL.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
WITH THAT MAGNIFYING GLASS?
MELTING ANTS. SEE?
THEY BURN UP IN THE SUN.
THERE WAS AN INCIDENT
DURING A SCHOOL FIELD TRIP.
MARQUIS WAS ON THE BUS.
IT PULLED UP TO A STOPLIGHT.
AND SUDDENLY, A MAN
DRESSED LIKE A CLOWN...
GREEN HAIR, PURPLE
SUIT, BIG, UGLY SMILE...
HE JUMPED ON BOARD,
TOOK OVER THE BUS.
THE JOKER?
THERE WAS AN ENCOUNTER
WITH MY SON.
THE JOKER HAD THIS
ZAPPER ON HIS HAND.
- THE JOY BUZZER.
- WHATEVER IT'S CALLED.
HE PRESSED IT AGAINST
MY SON'S FOREHEAD,
AND AN ELECTRICAL CHARGE
WENT THROUGH HIS BRAIN.
AFTER THAT DAY,
HE WAS DIFFERENT, DARK,
HORRIFYING.
MARQUIS? NO. MARQUIS HAS
BEEN NOTHING BUT NICE TO ME.
SOCIOPATHS ARE CHARMING
95% OF THE TIME, RYAN.
MOM, DON'T BE SO LAME.
IT'S NOT LAME TO TELL
YOUR DAD HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
I WROTE HIM A CARD!
SWEETHEART, YOUR
FATHER'S OVERSEAS,
AND IT WOULD MEAN SO MUCH TO HIM
- IF HE HEARD IT FROM YOUR...
- I SAID NO!
SPECIALISTS, NEUROLOGISTS,
PSYCHOLOGISTS.
I HAVE SPENT MILLIONS TRYING
TO FIX HIM BEHIND HIS BACK
SO I COULD HAVE
MY SWEET BOY AGAIN,
BUT NO ONE'S BEEN ABLE
TO HELP ME,
AND THEN I LEARNED
OF CRYOSTASIS.
SO YOU WERE BEHIND
THE FREEZE SERUM.
I HAD NO IDEA MY RESEARCH TEAM
WAS CONDUCTING
HUMAN EXPERIMENTS.
I JUST THOUGHT IF I COULD
SIDELINE MARQUIS FOR A WHILE
IT WOULD BUY ME SOME
TIME TO FIND A SOLUTION.
HE'S GOING IN FOR ANOTHER BITE.
HOW'S THE BURGER, DAD?
DELICIOUS.
WHAT THE HELL?
UH-OH. HE'S ON TO ME.
- IS THAT PEANUT BUTTER?
- HA HA HA!
WHAT'S WRONG?
PEANUTS. BURGER.
FRANKLIN, WHERE'S YOUR PEN?
WHERE'S YOUR PEN?
WHY ARE YOU TELLING ME THIS?
BECAUSE EVERYTHING I HAVE DONE
SINCE THE DAY WE MET
HAS BEEN TO PROTECT YOU, RYAN.
AND BECAUSE I NEED YOUR HELP.
ALL I WANT IS TO STOP MARQUIS
BEFORE ANYONE ELSE GETS HURT.
GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD!