Any other dormice
want to come out to play?
Hello, little friend.
Oh, my God.
You're Alice.
Correction.
I was Alice.
What is happening?
Oh, my God.
You're awake.
How am I here?
The Bat Team got wind
of your break-in.
Found you unconscious
underneath Marquis's pool table.
Beat the GCPD by a few seconds
and dumped you here.
You were...
You were out for a few hours.
I didn't know that you'd wake up.
Oh, Alice, are you okay?
Alice?
How do you feel?
I feel like Beth again.
We've gathered this morning
to discuss
the psychological evaluation
of Elizabeth Marie Kane.
This is the case
of a 13-year-old child
who after witnessing the grisly
decapitation of her mother
was abducted
and held against her will
by a madman.
After enduring 11 years
of his psychological
and physical torture
Beth escaped where she eventually
encountered a corrupt hypnotist
who compelled her
to fully break from her humanity.
As a result
Ms. Kane disassociated from reality
to become a character named Alice.
Well, when you put it like that...
For the past three weeks
the Gotham City
Psychological Association...
Is it just me or did they make Alice
sound like a victim?
I'm listening.
Our findings indicate
that after exposure
to a single electrical charge
Ms. Kane's brain
essentially rewired itself.
The area that had been cut off
from love and empathy
has been restored.
It is our recommendation to the court
that the criminal charges are dropped
and Ms. Kane be relieved of her trial
as we can no longer deem her
clinically insane.
Ms. Kane, where did you get
this magical buzzer?
Ryan. Ryan, I'm sorry.
Apologies.
You knew I needed that buzzer
for Marquis.
You knew I needed it for me.
The court of public opinion
may have changed their mind about you
but that doesn't change the truth.
Take it.
Maybe Luke can figure out a way
to make it work again.
It's fried, Alice. It's dead.
You won.
Ms. Kane,
how are you feeling about today?
Ms. Kane, what's next for you?
As much as I'd convinced myself
you were dead...
you were always there.
You just needed to be found.
I've always been a sucker
for a happy ending.
Ocean?
How are you...
You can't be here.
You mean because I'm dead?
Because of you?
That's the thing, Alice.
I don't think
you deserve a happy ending.
No, no, no.
What... What are you doing?
No. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It wasn't my fault.
I swear.
What is happening to me?
No...
Where is it?
Leave me alone!
Get away from me, Alice!
Get away!
What the...
Holy crap. You're Batwoman.
And you're Marquis Jet's
loyal number two.
In every morning before sunrise.
Never takes a sick day.
Keeper of Marquis's schedule
and, shall I presume, his secrets?
Hey.
So if you leave me alone in bed
you better have coffee.
Cream and sugar, dear?
Alice?
What are you doing here?
I have patients coming in.
Alice!
Where's the haloperidol?
The chlorpromazine?
The antipsychotics, Mar-Bear.
Cough them up.
I thought you were leaving.
I packed you a bag.
I gave you enough cash
to get halfway across this country.
Alice, there's an APB on your head.
You can't be here!
I am losing my mind!
I'm... I'm losing my mind.
The... The hallucinations are back,
but worse, I...
I just need a little edger
until you get me the Joy Buzzer.
But Kiki, she said that
there's only one buzz left.
Exactly,
so why are we still standing here?
Because Ryan needs it
for her brother.
But you need it for your sister.
Except you're not my sister.
Why didn't you stop me?
A real sister would've stopped me
before I killed someone!
You think this is my fault?
That was all you.
Poison Mary.
I was there for you,
making sure no one got in your way.
You weren't there for me,
you took advantage of me.
You needed me,
so you encouraged me.
And... and now a wife
is without her husband
and there are two boys
without their dad
and their life is ruined
and my life is ruined!
Got it.
I am so sorry that you gutted a man
with a tree branch.
My bad!
Would you just get the hell
out of here?
What is this, Gilmore Girls?
Ryan and I have some family matters
to discuss.
You mean you need her protection
from Marquis.
Now that the evidence of him
killing his father has been destroyed
you don't have anything
to hold over his head.
Ryan's life is complicated enough
without you playing Mom
all of a sudden.
The only one who's playing here
is Marquis
and if we don't get our hands
on that Joy Buzzer
and use it on him soon
all of Gotham City
could become his sandbox.
You know, maybe if you had
treated him like a criminal
and not your precious baby boy
we wouldn't be in this situation
to begin with.
- Maybe we wouldn't be...
- Do you really think...
Tell me
that is not vegan puff pastry.
Hey, you could've warned me
your mom was coming over.
At least when I lived with Alice,
she knocked.
Your mama almost saw me naked.
I am sorry. I...
I should've said something.
She wanted to huddle so we can
game-plan a way to stop Marquis.
- What's all this?
- This is Marquis's calendar.
Step one, we get a sense of his day,
so step two, we can ambush his ass.
- What's wrong?
- There's nothing on his schedule.
Yeah, but look at tomorrow
and every day last week.
He's booked solid 9 to 6,
meetings, lunches, calls, drinks.
Is there something special
about today?
Not that I know of.
Wait.
- Who's Barbara Kean?
- Why?
He emailed Miles,
asking him to find her home address.
Okay, Barbara Kean is the owner
of an art gallery in the Bowery
and Jim Gordon's ex-wife.
As in Commissioner Gordon?
Yeah, apparently, they used to dine
with Gotham's upper crust
but divorced after their son JJ was
found with body parts in his closet.
Barbara's reputation never recovered.
Probably for the best.
I'm actually late for my 8.00,
so I'll get going.
Wait, what happened
to finding Marquis?
Well, I will keep an ear
to the ground
and you'll do the same.
And whatever you need...
resources, money, manpower,
you got it, it's yours.
That was weird, right?
What?
Stay here.
- Where you going?
- Just give me two minutes.
I don't know how he knows
or what he's doing
but if it involves Barbara
it could very well involve you,
me, Mario, all of us.
Let your security teams know
we're not safe.
From whom?
BGS?
How'd you get down here so fast?
It's a lesbian bar. Know your exits.
Why didn't you tell Ryan
that Barbara Kean is part
of the Black Glove Society?
This doesn't need to involve Ryan.
Worried her knowing you're still
affiliated with a murderous cabal
might screw up
mother-daughter bonding time?
Despite appearances, Sophie,
I'm trying to do what's right.
Now excuse me
before people get hurt.
Ryan wants to trust you.
You're not even giving her a chance.
If you care about Ryan,
you'll keep this to yourself.
Hi. Can I ask who you're here
to pick up?
Who are you?
Is it Jada Jet?
Why are you asking me that?
Call 911.
Your boss was just kidnapped.
Oh, my God.
- Hi.
- Can I help you?
Is your mom home?
Mom, door!
Noah, you're gonna wake up
your little brother.
Sorry, if you're here to sell
something, it's not a good time.
Oh, no, I'm not selling anything.
I'm Mary Hamilton.
I'm sorry to stop by unannounced
when your family is going through
such a difficult time.
Yes?
I believe I have information
pertaining to your husband's death.
Come in.
Look who's losing her grip.
Figuratively and literally.
My sweet Mouse.
No.
Did you think this was over?
I am not listening to you.
You're not here, and you're not real.
What are you doing here?
Trying to get yourself
a little Joy Buzzer?
An undo switch?
Wouldn't that be nice?
Get out of my head...
You didn't really think
you've seen the last of me, did you?
Okay.
The good news is black Rolls-Royce
with cranberry leather interior
are rare even for rich people.
This was targeted.
I mean, how else would someone know
the identical make and model
of Jada's car?
Speaking of identical,
weren't you wearing that yesterday?
Actually, I...
Helped me track down
Marquis' assistant all night.
She didn't have time to go home.
Okay. Got a hit.
Partial plate belongs to a car
purchased two days ago
by Wayne Enterprises.
Marquis. He made his move.
Call me crazy
but I think this has something to do
with Barbara Kean
and the Black Glove Society.
Explain to me on the road.
Luke, give me a trace on that car.
We need to know where the hell
he's taking her ASAP.
On it.
Make me a Joy Buzzer
and this could be an exciting tale
to tell the grandkids
around the campfire.
Nice try
but nothing beats the one
about the time
I helped the Joker
beat Robin to death with a crowbar.
Holiday family classic.
See, the thing is, sweetie...
I only have the patience
to work for one psychopath
and unfortunately for you,
Marquis Jet signs my W2s.
A little tip
about managing psychopaths.
It's best to appease the one
who has the knife at your throat.
I've worked for the Joker
since I was 16.
You think you're the first
crazy blonde woman
I've ever dealt with?
Sorry about that.
Way too many crazy people
in this room.
Of course, it's in her pocket.
She was making
some last-minute tweaks for me.
Alice of freaking Wonderland.
May I just say, it is an honor.
Marquis Jet, I presume.
In the flesh. Don't steal it.
So, Alice of freaking Wonderland,
what could you possibly want
with my Joy Buzzer?
Here's the thing. That's...
That's one more buzz in it.
And if you play
your razor-sharp cards right
it doesn't have to be used on you.
Pretty please, tell me you didn't
wanna use it on yourself.
I mean, you're a legend.
You're the Menace of Gotham.
The Ring Leader of Rabbits.
The Queen of Heartlessness.
Like you said, too many crazies,
too small a space.
Now give me...
The thing is, Alice...
you know, I might be new to this
whole world of public psychos
but I'm not about to start my reign
by losing one of the legends.
Let's see
if I can't change your mind.
What in the cult from hell?
Ladies and gentlemen
of the Black Glove Society
thank you for joining me
this evening.
Now in honor of tradition,
let us commence with roll call.
Barbara Kean?
Here.
Then we have Burton Crowne.
Nice stache, bro.
Next.
One of the biggest profiteers
of crazy...
Mr. Jeremiah Arkham himself.
Mario Falcone, welcome.
And last but certainly not least
the lady who was responsible
for this fine evening.
Ms. Jada Jet.
Now allow me to welcome you
to the Black Glove Society's
final ceremony.
Go on, look around.
The person to your right
and the person to your left
are going to die tonight.
We having fun yet?
So as I've recently come to discover
the Black Glove Society
was founded by Marla Elliot in 1984.
Her son Tommy
had this deeply creepy need
to be just like
his bestie Bruce Wayne.
Even wanted to be an orphan
like Bruce.
Which meant he went at Mommy
with her sewing scissors.
"Uh-oh!" said Marla Elliot...
hiding her stab wounds
behind her plastic surgery.
"I'm Gotham's high society.
I can't have a freak show for a son.
What if somebody stops inviting me
to lunches at the polo club?
Guess we got to do something
about that, right?"
And thus...
the Black Glove Society was born.
Am I getting this right so far?
Nod if I'm close.
- Yeah.
- Good.
Barbara Kean.
Now you're the mother
of JJ Gordon, right?
If I'm remembering this correctly,
when JJ was 15
he tied a labradoodle
to train tracks?
That's... That's rough, you know?
Because what happens
when you run for philanthropic chair
and somebody's like...
"Hey, didn't your kid murder
a freaking labradoodle?"
So to hide an unsightly scene,
you hired some off-the-books doctors
to fill JJ
with experimental medication
so you could try to fix him.
Problem is, shocker, it didn't work.
Now he's just a drooling husk
in Arkham.
Jada, what the hell is happening?
You... You need to do something.
- Oh, come on.
- Please.
Don't fight it, Babs.
I mean, you did use this
on your own son.
So how dangerous could it be, right?
Seven clinical trials in all.
This dose contains
every single ingredient
of every single medicine
you've given him.
I'm sorry.
Say hi to Marla for us, would you?
Who's next?
You know, I bet he would let you
kill a few of them.
- Mario Falcone.
- He seems to really like you.
I'm good. Thanks.
You sure?
Isn't this sort of thing
kind of like your Super Bowl?
Revenge. Flair.
A fun little wheel to make it a game.
Why are you here?
The Joy Buzzer, Alice.
You don't deserve that.
Plain and simple.
See, that's confusing.
Because you are a figment
of my delirium
and I know in my bones
that I not only deserve it,
I need it.
So be gone, sweet Mouse.
Your logic doesn't fit
into my working narrative.
You poisoned me...
at our tea party.
You taped a live rat to my chest
to lure bats to my flesh...
my blood.
That's what you did
to your best friend.
Do you think you could just
walk away from that?
Erase it? Move on?
Get away from me!
So you said you had information
about my husband's murder?
Right.
So...
This is difficult.
But...
I know your husband's killer.
- So do we.
- You do?
It's very brave of you, Mary,
to come here
considering your stepsister
took his life.
I'm sorry, what?
I figured that's why you came here.
Yesterday, the police informed us
they received a call from a woman
claiming to be Alice.
She owned up to the murder.
They're still confirming
all the facts
but it adds up.
She knew the exact location,
the cause.
And the description matches
what my youngest told us.
That he saw a woman with blonde hair
attack my husband.
I... I assume
that's what you were here to tell us?
Yes.
That.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
For how I responded with Luke.
I froze.
Not a big deal.
Maybe a little bit of a deal though.
I'm not saying we need to shout
anything from rooftops
but you have to admit
there's a difference
between keeping something private
and hiding something.
I wasn't hiding anything.
It was none of his business.
Batwing to Batmobile.
Batwing, we're here. Status update?
Had a match on our car.
It's parked on the edge of a cemetery
on the other side of Gotham U.
Just sent you the coordinates.
Okay, thanks.
I wonder who we got next.
Marquis. Marquis. Stop.
Does that look familiar?
Just...
You... You don't have
to do this, son.
I'm gonna freeze you
like you tried to freeze me, Mom.
It's gonna be just like
you always used to say.
Go stand in a corner
and think about what you've done.
You're gonna have decades
to do exactly that.
Except they're not gonna be
pleasant thoughts.
They're gonna be
the thoughts of a woman
who is more like her crazy son
than she'd ever like to admit.
Marquis...
- Welcome to the club, Jada Jet.
- Marquis. Marquis, don't.
- We're all mad here.
- Don't.
Damn. I throw you a party,
and this is how you thank me?
Give it to me.
Or, or...
we rule Gotham together.
You could be the Harley to my Joker.
I think you have that backwards.
Besides, we come from
different schools of loony tune.
Is that what you really think?
You have no idea, do you?
2003.
My second grade class
was on a field trip.
And all of a sudden, out of nowhere,
someone bangs on the door
and lo and behold,
it's the freaking Joker.
He blows the bus driver's head off.
Now I realized nobody
was gonna do anything to help.
So I thought, you know,
maybe it should be me.
So I walked up to him, terrified,
but acting all brave.
And he looks down at me
with his deformed smile
and then he just starts
laughing and laughing.
Then the Joker leans in,
and he says...
"I'm taking you kids to
Amusement Mile
where I'm hiding the biggest
acid bomb you've ever seen.
And Gotham City
is gonna rain chemicals
until everybody looks like the Joker."
Next thing I know...
somebody yells
that Batman's following us.
And there was this...
there was this car in front of us
driving hella slow.
I just heard the Joker
revving his engine.
You were on the bus that drove
my mom's car off the bridge.
Alice,
that's what I'm trying to tell you.
It's fate.
You and I were born on the same day.
You hear that, Mom?
I guess that means
today is your birthday.
Buckle up.
What if I were to give you something
that would make the Joker
wish he were you?
That's not yours.
Thank God.
- Where is he?
- I don't know. He just left.
You should've told me
about Black Glove.
I could've helped.
And risk losing you all over again?
You need to get out of here now.
- I'm not leaving you with him.
- Go.
Give me the buzzer, Alice.
Why are you here?
We need it for Marquis.
Says who? Jada?
The woman who turned your sister
into Olaf?
I'm not doing it for Jada.
I'm doing it to stop Marquis
from wreaking hell across this city.
Well, if it's hell that you want...
you've come to the right girl.
I'm sorry, I know you said
to never touch your gun
but it's so alluring.
That is so unfair.
What are you doing? Let go of me!
No. No, no, no. No.
That's mine!
He didn't...
Just help me, please.
Don't make me go back there.
Don't make me go back to Arkham.
Barbara? Barbara Kean. Wake up.
I'm gonna get you help, okay?
Just stay with me.
- I don't wanna hurt you.
- Hurt me?
But you wore a super suit here
because it's cute?
Look at you,
just a coward hiding her face.
Otherwise, everyone'll know
she's just a punk-ass street rat
whose own mommy didn't want her.
- That better?
- Oh, look at you, tough girl.
I'm not competing with you, Marquis.
Oh, is this the part
where you tell me it's not my fault?
That I'm a victim,
that you feel sorry for me?
I don't feel sorry for you.
When I first learned about you,
I was jealous of you.
You had everything.
Security, love, family, a future.
Oh, yeah, my brain was scrambled eggs
but hey, Disneyland FastPass,
am I right?
You grew up believing
you could be anyone
that you could do anything.
I was jealous I didn't get that.
Till I realized
I had something you didn't have.
- Hope.
- I have hope.
I got hope coming out of my ears,
Wilder.
For example.
I was hoping that didn't kill you.
So I can freeze your ass
alongside Mom.
That's enough.
Don't make me do this, Marquis.
What are you gonna do?
Shoot your own son?
You're not my son.
Not anymore.
Thought I told you to run.
Nice try, baby girl...
but I'm not making
that mistake again.
So I've never been in an "out"
relationship with a girl.
Okay.
So we're doing this.
Just hear me out.
I've never introduced a girl
to my friends
or had to get Jordan's approval
or, God help us all,
had a girl meet my mom.
So that's what today triggered
for me.
What if I finally find the courage
to be out
but the person I'm interested in
doesn't want the same thing?
One, I'm pretty sure Jordan loves me.
And two...
you're right.
I was hiding.
Not from Luke, from myself.
Because every time
I get something good
I end up losing it.
Well, that's not gonna
happen this time.
You're gonna make me
meet your mom, aren't you?
Do I need to remind you what happened
the night I met your mom?
You owe me big time.
Okay.
Can I wear the Batsuit at least?
I'm the one she's gonna
try to kill, not you.
She's gonna be trying to tell me
that do all this other stuff that...
Well, Marquis ditched the Rolls.
So we lost eyes on him.
Knowing him, he won't stay
off the radar very long.
So we call the police, smoke him out
before he makes his next move?
I'm not letting him rot in Arkham
for the rest of his life.
Look, we have the buzzer.
Alice can't take it from us.
Give me 24 hours.
If I can't stop Marquis, then fine,
take it out of my hand.
But I deserve one shot.
Sorry, weren't you wearing that
yesterday?
Oh, my God, you too?
What is with the fashion police
today?
Are... Are you two...
Wait. No.
Hang on.
Wait.
No... My God. You are, aren't you?
Sorry, what is happening?
Ryan and Sophie are totally a thing.
Seriously?
Yeah.
We're officially a thing.
This is...
Okay. Yay!
I actually can't remember
the last time I heard good news
so...
Are you okay right now?
Why are we still here?
We're leaving. Okay?
So you two can have
the whole place to yourselves
to be all cute and coupley.
Oh, my God.
How did I not know?
Okay. Come on.
You figured it out yet?
We're never gonna leave you.
Should have buzzed yourself
when you had the chance, Alice.
You're the one who stopped me?
Exactly.
So that every second of every day
we can be here to remind you
what you did to us.
Please go away.
Just go away!
I said get away from me!
Are you real?
Yes. Yes, Alice, I'm real.
Yeah, I told the facility that
I was your personal physician.
You have to get me out of here.
I had to come
and say thank you.
What you did for me...
it was above and beyond anything
that anyone's ever done for me.
Thank you.
That's one more on the resume.
Consider it a parting gift.
Hey.
You don't have to deflect.
I know you're trying.
I'm sorry, Mary.
It's okay.
No.
I'm really...
I'm really sorry.
What did you do?
Let's have some fun.