SHE'S NOT HERE.
YOU STAY SHARP, MONTOYA.
PAMELA ISLEY...
SHOW YOURSELF!
SURRENDER, OR WE WILL USE FORCE!
I'M RIGHT HERE.
STOP! PLEASE.
PLEASE DON'T MAKE ME DO THIS.
TAKE THE SHOT, MONTOYA.
NO!
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO! NO!
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
BECAUSE SOMEONE HAS TO CARE.
FLORA & FAWNA:
VERY FEW PEOPLE CAN PULL
OFF GREEN WITH ANY SWAGGER,
BUT I ACTUALLY DON'T
HATE THIS FOR YOU.
AHH. YEAH. IT'S INTERESTING.
I, UM... I'M SORRY.
I'VE NEVER BEEN
IN A POSITION BEFORE
WHERE I COULDN'T
BE HONEST BECAUSE I WAS
WORRIED ABOUT HURTING SOMEONE'S
FEELINGS, SO I'M STALLING.
AW! I THINK THAT'S
THE SWEETEST THING
YOU'VE EVER SAID TO ME.
- DID YOU ORDER MORE FOOD?
- NO.
- DID YOU ORDER MORE STRIPPERS?
- UM...
MS. HAMILTON,
IT'S TIME TO ASK YOU
TO PACK YOUR THINGS
AND PART WAYS WITH US.
UM, RUDE.
YOU'VE RACKED UP AN $8,000 BILL
WITHOUT SHOWING
ANY ABILITY TO PAY FOR IT.
OH! I TOLD THE LADY
AT THE DESK 10 TIMES
TRY ALL MY OTHER CARDS.
THEY'VE ALL BEEN DECLINED,
MS. HAMILTON.
OH, ACTUALLY, IT'S DR. HAMILTON.
IT'S NOT MS.
I'M AFRAID I NEED
TO ASK YOU TO LEAVE,
OR THE METROPOLIS PD
WILL BE ESCORTING YOU OUT.
THIS IS ALL A MISUNDERSTANDING.
GIVE ME SOME TIME
TO FIGURE IT OUT.
PLEASE TAKE ALL THE TIME
YOU NEED.
WE'LL ACCEPT YOUR APOLOGY
AND A COMPLIMENTARY BOTTLE
OF DOM
FOR THE INCONVENIENCE.
YOU'RE VERY KIND, MA'AM.
HA! I KNOW.
DID THE BAT BITCHES CUT ME OFF?
ALL YOUR FANCY DEGREES, AND
YOU DIDN'T SEE THAT COMING?
I THOUGHT WE WERE PAST THIS.
I MEAN, ONE WOULD THINK
THAT NEARLY VINE-SQUEEZING
THE LIFE OUT OF YOUR BESTIE
AND THEN CRUSHING
THE ONLY CURE
FOR YOU IN EXISTENCE
WAS A PRETTY GOOD INDICATOR
THAT IT WAS TIME TO MOVE ON
FROM THE FRIENDSHIP.
ANYONE ELSE FIND IT IRONIC
THAT WHEN I BEG
RYAN AND LUKE
FOR THEIR ATTENTION
THEY'RE TOO BUSY
WITH THEIR OWN DRAMA,
BUT THEN WHEN I FINALLY
STEP AWAY
FOR SOME MUCH-NEEDED ME TIME,
MARY HAMILTON IS THE COVETED
BATMISSION OF THE WEEK?
IF THIS IS A LECTURE ON
BEING BATWOMAN'S MOST WANTED,
TRUST ME, I ALREADY
TOOK THE EXAM.
WELL, WHAT DO I DO?
UH, YOU KILL THEM IMMEDIATELY.
ALICE.
FINE. AS SOMEONE WHO HAD A
SO-CALLED FAMILY MEMBER OBSESSED
WITH THE IDEA THAT
I COULD CHANGE,
HERE'S WHAT YOU DO.
YOU MAKE YOUR FRIENDS
HATE YOU SO MUCH
THAT THEY WANT TO
GIVE UP ON YOU.
FLOWERS AREN'T A FIX-ALL, PAM.
MY PARTNER LOST A KIDNEY.
BUT THEY'RE WHITE TULIPS.
TECHNICALLY FROM
THE LILIACEAE FAMILY.
THEY SYMBOLIZE FORGIVENESS.
WOULD YOU RATHER IT BE A KIDNEY?
HA!
I'M TRYING HERE, RENEE.
HE COULD HAVE DIED.
HE WAS GOING TO SHOOT ME.
BECAUSE I COULDN'T.
I'M SUPPOSED TO HAVE HIS BACK.
NO. YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO HAVE MY BACK.
OHH. DON'T YOU SEE
HOW UNFAIR THAT IS?
I TOOK AN OATH
TO UPHOLD THE LAW,
AND YOU'RE OUT THERE
BREAKING IT CONSTANTLY
FOR THE SAKE OF WHAT...
MOTHER NATURE?
I KNOW GLOBAL WARMING,
WATER SHORTAGE,
EXTINCTION OF SPECIES IS
AN INCONVENIENT THOUGHT FOR YOU,
BUT UNFORTUNATELY,
THIS REUSABLE COFFEE MUG
ISN'T THE SOLUTION.
WHAT IS THE SOLUTION THEN?
QUITTING YOUR JOB,
OSTRACIZING OUR FRIENDS,
BECOMING SO OBSESSED
TO THE POINT
WHERE I DON'T EVEN
RECOGNIZE YOU?
ARE YOU COMING WITH ME OR NOT?
NOT IF YOU GO WHERE
I CAN'T FOLLOW YOU.
STAY HERE. STAY THE...
QUIRKY, BRILLIANT SCIENTIST
WHO LOVES READING AND BASEBALL
THAT I FELL IN LOVE
WITH A DECADE AGO.
SHE'S GONE.
SHE'S BLOSSOMED INTO SOMEONE
WHO CAN STAND UP FOR HERSELF
AND, MORE IMPORTANTLY,
FOR THOSE THINGS THAT CAN'T.
I FROZE MARY'S BANK ACCOUNTS.
I THINK.
INTERNET'S CUT OUT 10 TIMES.
AND NOW I HAVE
THE SPINNING WHEEL OF DEATH.
THAT'S... AWESOME.
DOES ASBESTOS HAVE A SMELL?
ANYONE SMELL THAT?
DEAD RAT IN THE WALL.
GIVE IT 3 DAYS. IT'LL PASS.
WE DON'T HAVE 3 DAYS.
YOU SAW HER CLINIC.
IT'S COMPLETELY
OVERRUN BY PLANT LIFE.
YOU DON'T FIND THAT SYMBOLIC?
WE WON'T LET HER FORGET
WHO SHE IS.
OH, HOPE. THAT'S SWEET.
HOW'S THAT WORKING OUT FOR YOU?
I'M SORRY. I LEFT
MY SARCASM METER
IN THE BATCAVE I NO LONGER
HAVE ACCESS TO.
IS THERE SOMETHING YOU
WOULD LIKE TO SAY TO ME?
TAKE OFF THE KID GLOVES, RYAN.
- KID GLOVES?
- YOU WOULDN'T HAVE MARQUIS
ARRESTED BECAUSE HE'S FAMILY.
YOU UNDERESTIMATED MARY
BECAUSE SHE'S YOUR FRIEND,
AND NOW YOU'RE LOCKED
OUT OF YOUR BATCAVE
AND YOUR BESTIE'S ON THE LAM
WITH A SERIAL KILLER.
JUMP IN IF I'M MISSING ANYTHING.
OK. WHAT THE HELL
WAS I SUPPOSED TO DO,
PUMMEL MARY WITH BATARANGS,
LET THEM THROW MARQUIS
IN ARKHAM FOR A BRAIN INJURY
THAT ISN'T HIS FAULT?
IT'S CALLED MAKING HARD CHOICES.
WHY ARE WE EVEN HERE?
THERE WASN'T A TOXIC SEWER
WITH WI-FI ACCESS?
RENEE'S NOT WRONG, RYAN.
WE NEED A HARDER STANCE.
BY AGREEING WITH THE WOMAN
WHO'S BLACKMAILING ME
BECAUSE YOU'RE
SLEEPING WITH HER?
AHEM. WOW. UM, I THINK
I SMELL THAT ASBESTOS.
MAYBE WE SHOULD GO GET SOME AIR.
LOOK. I GET IT.
MARY'S YOUR FRIEND.
I THOUGHT I COULD PLEAD AND HOPE
AND RATIONALIZE WITH PAM, TOO.
IT DIDN'T WORK.
EVENTUALLY, IT GOT TO THE POINT
WHERE SHE MADE ME CHOOSE...
MY OBLIGATION
TO THE CITY OR HER.
SO WHAT DID YOU DO?
SOMETHING PAM WILL NEVER
FORGIVE ME FOR.
I SOLD MY SOUL TO BATMAN.
HE KNEW HE COULDN'T
TRUST ARKHAM TO CONTAIN HER,
SO HE DEVELOPED
A DESICCATION SERUM
THAT MIMICKED THE PROCESS
A PLANT GOES THROUGH
WHEN IT'S DENIED
WATER OR SUNLIGHT.
THE DEVICE USED TO INJECT IT
IS CODED TO THE SERUM,
MEANING IT'S ALSO
THE ONLY WAY
TO EXTRACT IT FROM HER.
SO IF WE GOT MORE OF THE SERUM,
WE COULD USE IT ON MARY?
I HAVE THE DEVICE,
BUT HE ONLY MADE
ONE DOSE OF SERUM.
IT'S CURRENTLY PUMPING THROUGH
PAMELA'S BLOODSTREAM.
- SO WHERE IS SHE?
- NO ONE KNOWS.
OK, BUT IF WE FIND HER,
THEN PRESUMABLY
WE COULD SIPHON THE SERUM
AND USE IT TO STOP MARY, RIGHT?
WRONG! FIRST OF ALL,
ACCIDENTALLY UNLEASHING
AN ECOTERRORIST WOULD NOT
BE A GOOD LOOK FOR US.
SECOND, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT DESICCATION MEANS?
WE WOULD BE DEHYDRATING
MARY TO THE BRINK OF DEATH.
NO. THE SERUM
WAS JUST TO PUT PAM DOWN,
AND THAT WAS 10 YEARS AGO.
IF WE REMOVE IT,
MY GUESS IS SHE STAYS DORMANT
UNLESS SHE COMES INTO CONTACT
WITH SUNLIGHT OR WATER.
AS FOR POINT NUMBER TWO,
KID GLOVES, RYAN.
DID YOU HEAR WHAT
RENEE JUST SAID?
PAM WILL NEVER FORGIVE HER
FOR WHAT SHE DID TO HER.
WE ARE NOT PUTTING MARY
THROUGH THAT SAME TORTURE
SO SHE CAN HATE US, TOO.
THIS COULD BE
OUR ONLY CHANCE TO SAVE MARY.
THE TRUE MARY WOULD WANT
US TO STOP HER
BEFORE SHE CAN DO SOMETHING
THAT SHE CAN'T TAKE BACK.
WE CANNOT HELP HER
UNLESS WE STOP HER.
FINE.
IF I WERE BATMAN,
WHERE WOULD I STASH POISON IVY?
OUR BEST BET IS THAT
BRUCE WROTE ABOUT PAM ISLEY
IN HIS JOURNALS,
WHICH ARE IN THE BATCAVE HERE,
BUT MARQUIS'
STATE-OF-THE-ART INTERIOR
AND EXTERIOR CAMERAS MEANS
NO ROOF, BALCONY,
OR GARAGE ACCESS.
CAN YOU HACK INTO THE FEED
AND BUY ME SOME TIME?
- NOT WITH DIALUP.
- MANPOWER?
THERE'S 5 SECURITY
GUARDS PER FLOOR.
- DIGITAL UPGRADES?
- ACCORDING TO OUR FORMER STAFF,
EVERY EXECUTIVE ELEVATOR
REQUIRES A THUMB SCAN,
AND HIS OFFICE IS LOCKED
WITH A RETINAL SCAN.
GUYS, WE'RE NOT
GETTING INTO THIS BUILDING.
WHY IS MARQUIS CALLING ME?
AM I SUPPOSED TO TAKE THIS?
WHAT THE HELL DOES HE WANT?
GUESS I'M ABOUT TO FIND OUT.
I'M SORRY. I WAS
A DETECTIVE FOR 8 YEARS,
AND I'M JUST LEARNING NOW
THAT...
BRUCE WAYNE WAS... BATMAN?
WHAT UP, SIS?
QUICK QUESTION FOR YOU.
IS THIS THING LEGIT?
WHAT DO YOU THINK
I CAN HAWK IT FOR,
A BUCK 50, TWO?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, MARQUIS?
I'M REDECORATING MY OFFICE.
YOU DO KNOW YOU HAD
A CHESS SET, RIGHT?
YOU SHOULD BE IN JAIL.
OH! SAMESIES, SIS.
REMEMBER WHEN YOU
HAD ME KIDNAPPED?
THAT'S ILLEGAL! TSK, TSK, TSK.
YOU WANT TO CALL IT SIXES
AND MOVE ON?
YOU NEED HELP.
YOU NEED A DOCTOR.
IT'S NOT TOO LATE.
- HOLD THAT THOUGHT.
- SIR.
THE PLANNER'S UPSTAIRS
READY TO TAKE YOU
THROUGH THE STAGING
FOR THE PARTY TONIGHT,
AND YOUR MASK IS HERE
FOR A FITTING.
YEAH. TWO SECONDS.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
YOU WERE CALLING ME
A MENTAL CASE.
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE CALLED ME
IF A TINY PART OF YOU WASN'T
REACHING OUT FOR HELP.
JUST LIKE THERE'S
A TINY PART OF YOU
THAT LOVES ME, RIGHT,
OR ELSE YOU WOULD HAVE HAD
MY ASS THROWN IN ARKHAM,
AND BECAUSE YOU LOVE ME,
YOU TRIED TO TURN ME
INTO AN ICE CUBE.
ANYWAY, I JUST WANTED TO
SAY THANK YOU.
THE COLD,
THE NEAR DEATH OF IT ALL,
GOT TO SAY,
IT AWOKE SOMETHING IN ME
BECAUSE I'VE NEVER FELT
THIS ALIVE.
MARQUIS JET IS COMING
FOR YOU, GOTHAM!
YOU'LL BE HEARING FROM ME SOON.
WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT?
I THINK MARQUIS IS THROWING
A PARTY AT WAYNE TONIGHT,
AND WE'RE GONNA CRASH IT.
SO WE SHOULD RUN
OUR IDENTITIES. GO.
AHEM. HELLO. I'M SPENCER GLAD,
FORMER OLYMPIC ATHLETE,
RUMORED TO BE
THE NEXT OWNER
OF THE GOTHAM KNIGHTS.
I'LL HIT YOU UP
FOR FLOOR SEATS, SPENCE.
THE NAME'S CECELIA LANGLEY,
HEIRESS TO A WHISKEY FORTUNE
AND WORLD TRAVELER.
PENELOPE DEVEREAUX,
WHO FOR SOME REASON
RUNS A BOARD GAME EMPIRE?
- HONESTLY, DREAM JOB.
- JUST GONNA SAY IT.
MY GIRL SOUNDS HOT.
ALSO, HOW ARE WE NOT GONNA
RUN INTO THESE PEOPLE TONIGHT?
YEAH. I SENT SOME E-MAILS.
THEY THINK THEY'RE UNINVITED,
AND, YES, SHE IS.
I FITTED YOUR MASK
WITH OCULAR MESH SCANNERS
FROM THE BATSUIT.
BE CAREFUL. SOPHIE, YOURS IS
FROM THE DOLLAR STORE.
- GO NUTS.
- OK. SO WE GET IN,
GET PAST SECURITY,
GET TO THE BATCAVE,
FIND BRUCE'S JOURNALS,
AND FIND PAM.
OH, AND, PENELOPE,
YOU'RE FRENCH.
WAIT. WHAT?
8 OF CLUBS? WHAT'S THIS ABOUT?
HOPEFULLY WE'LL BE LONG
GONE BEFORE IT MATTERS.
MARQUIS, ON P.A.:
WHO WANTS TO PLAY A GAME?
THERE'S NOTHING WORSE IN LIFE
THAN A FAKE SMILE.
A COUPLE DAYS AGO, I SAT DOWN
AT THE TABLE
OF MY BRAND-NEW BOARD ROOM,
SURROUNDED BY MEN AND WOMEN
WHO WERE SUPPOSED TO BE
MY SOLDIERS,
AND THEY TOLD ME THAT
I WASN'T THE RIGHT MAN
TO LEAD WAYNE ENTERPRISES.
ON YOUR RIGHT.
OH, OH, MAN. OH. I'M SO SORRY.
HI. I'LL TAKE THIS FOR YOU.
BUT IT WAS THE WAY
THAT THEY SAID IT.
NO CRACK OR ANYTHING.
THAT'S CRAZY.
SO CONDESCENDING,
LIKE THEY WERE MAD ABOUT IT,
LIKE THIS.
SO I FIRED THEIR ASSES!
EACH OF YOU HAS PROVEN
TO BE OF SAVAGE MIND.
THAT'S WHO I WANT
AT MY WAYNE ENTERPRISES.
JACK OF HEARTS.
DID WE JUST CRASH A DERANGED
GROUP JOB INTERVIEW?
I'M AFRAID SO.
HANDS ON THE TABLE,
JACK OF HEARTS.
TRUE OR FALSE...
WHEN WE CLIMB TO THE TOP,
WE GOT TO BE WILLING
TO GET A LITTLE CRAZY.
TRUE.
HOW'S THIS? CLOSE ENOUGH?
NO. WE NEED A FULL RETINAL
MAP TO FOOL THE SCANNERS.
YOU NEED TO BE A LOT CLOSER.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO DO THAT
WHILE HE'S PLAYING
GAME SHOW HOST?
LOOK. ALL I KNOW IS
I SWITCHED THE SIM CARD
ON HIS ASSISTANT'S TABLET,
AND NOW I HAVE
FULL ACCESS
TO TOWER SECURITY CAMS.
OK. AHEM.
IT'S NOT A COMPETITION.
YEAH. SURE THING,
BUT, UH, SOPHIE JUST GOT
MARQUIS' THUMBPRINT, SO KIND
OF JUST WAITING ON YOU HERE.
COMPLETE THIS SENTENCE.
THE SICK AMONG US DESERVE OUR...
PITY?
HA HA HA!
HA HA HA! HA HA HA!
THE ANSWER WE WERE
LOOKING FOR WAS FEAR.
TOUGH LUCK.
WHO'S NEXT?
COME ON. DON'T BE SHY.
LOOK. I PROMISE THIS IS
THE OPPORTUNITY OF A LIFETIME.
3 OF DIAMONDS.
OUI. C'EST MOI.
OH. MISS PENELOPE DEVEREAUX
I PRESUME.
OK. HERE WE GO.
THE ONLY PARISIAN
ON MY GUEST LIST.
YOU CREATED THE GAME
3 MURDERS AT THE BOWERY.
MAY I SAY YOUR WORK IS MOST...
THOUGHTFULLY DERANGED.
MERCI.
JUST... JUST A FEW MORE SECONDS.
TRUE OR FALSE...
AN ARTIST ALWAYS PUTS HERSELF,
NO MATTER HOW DARK,
INTO HER WORK.
OUI.
WHENEVER WE REVEAL
OUR DARKNESS INTO THE LIGHT.
WE ARE NO LONGER SCARED.
NON.
HEH.
FINISH THIS SENTENCE.
A MOTHER'S LOVE IS...
SCAN COMPLETE. GOOD TO GO.
EH, NOT MY PROBLEM.
YOU KNOW, IF MY
THERAPIST WERE HERE,
SHE'D SAY IT'S NEVER A GOOD IDEA
TO HUNT A DESICCATED BODY
WHILE ANGRY.
JUST TELL ME WHY SHE WANTS
TO BE HERE ALL OF A SUDDEN.
IT'S NOT ALL OF A SUDDEN.
WE WERE PLANNING TO SPEND
OUR ENTIRE LIVES TOGETHER.
BRUCE MENTIONED
ANYTHING ABOUT PAM,
THERE'S A GOOD CHANCE
I'LL UNDERSTAND IT.
JUST BECAUSE YOU WANT TO
KISS AND MAKE UP WITH HER
DOESN'T MEAN WE'RE GOOD.
I GET WHY YOU'RE PISSED,
BUT REMEMBER SOMETHING.
POISON IVY COST ME
THE LOVE OF MY LIFE.
TRYING TO HELP.
I'LL TAKE YOUR HELP.
THEN I WANT MY NAME...
BATWOMAN'S NAME...
OUT OF YOUR MOUTH.
WE'VE PRETTY MUCH CLEANED
UP EVERYTHING ON YOUR LIST.
THAT'S A FUN WAY OF SAYING
THE JOKER'S JOY BUZZER'S
STILL UNACCOUNTED FOR.
OK. WE NEED ALICE TO FIND IT.
WAIT. ALICE WAS YOUR JOB, RIGHT?
AND YOU WERE HOOKING UP
WITH HER AT HER PLACE,
WHICH... PHEW... I HOPE
IT'S NICER THAN HER OFFICE.
MY PLACE IS RENT CONTROLLED.
WHO CARES IF IT'S NICE?
REALLY THOUGHT WAYNE TOWER
WAS TALL ENOUGH
FOR US TO GET
TO HANDSHAKES, LADIES.
HI. HEY. I THOUGHT I TOLD
YOU TO LOCK THE DOOR.
EHH.
UHH!
WE'RE THE CLEANING LADIES.
LET'S GO.
SORRY ABOUT THE MESS.
CAN YOU FACE THE OTHER WAY?
WE KIND OF GOT A HIDDEN
ENTRY SITUATION GOING HERE.
LET'S HAVE SOME FUN.
GUYS, PLEASE TELL ME
YOU FIGURED OUT
WHERE POISON IVY'S BURIED.
- WE JUST GOT TO THE JOURNALS.
- BE QUICK ABOUT IT
BECAUSE MARY JUST GOT HERE.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
MARY CAME HOME.
IS SHE LOOKING FOR US?
UH, JUST JUDGING
A BOOK BY ITS COVER HERE,
BUT I THINK IT'S MORE
LIKELY THAT SHE'S LOOKING
FOR FREAK FERTILIZER.
ANY SIGN OF ALICE WITH HER?
NO, NOT YET, BUT I'LL KEEP
MY EYE ON THE SECURITY CAMS.
DON'T LET HER
LEAVE THIS BUILDING.
GREAT. I MEAN, SHE'S
BEEN SO COOPERATIVE LATELY,
I SEE NO PROBLEMS THERE.
OK. CALL IF YOU NEED BACKUP.
IF MARY'S HERE,
IT'S FOR A REASON,
AND I CAN ASSURE YOU
IT'S NOT TO DANCE.
LET'S JUST GET TO THESE.
OK. I PROMISE I JUST
WANT TO TALK.
OK. I'LL JUST GRAB
A NUMBER AND STAY RIGHT HERE.
MARY HAMILTON.
WELL, WELL. I SHOULD PROBABLY
FIRE MY PUBLICIST,
MARY HAMILTON,
BECAUSE YOU SHOULD KNOW YOUR
FRIENDS NO LONGER LIVE HERE.
WELL, I'M NO PR REP,
BUT IF SHE'S THE ONE
WHO CAME UP WITH YOUR
DECK OF CARDS THEME,
IT'S DEFINITELY SOMETHING
YOU SHOULD CONSIDER.
HEH. I'M NOT FEELING THE
VIBES YOU'RE PUTTING OUT,
AND THAT'S A SHAME
BECAUSE YOU...
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'D
BE A LOT OF FUN.
DON'T GIVE UP ON ME
SO FAST, MR. C-E-BRO.
YOU HAVEN'T EVEN HEARD THE REASON
I CAME ALL THIS WAY TO FIND YOU.
DANCE?
OK. OK. OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK.
WE DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS.
NEW PLAN. BRUCE ARCHIVED
THESE CHRONOLOGICALLY,
SO LET'S START THERE.
WHEN WAS THE FIRST TIME YOU
CONTACTED BATMAN FOR HELP?
IT WAS EARLY JUNE 2011.
OK.
DOES ANY OF THIS LOOK FAMILIAR?
THIS. THIS IS
THE GOTHAM CITY DAM.
BRUCE WOULDN'T HAVE DESICCATED
PAM AROUND THAT MUCH WATER.
HE DIDN'T. HE NEEDED TO
STOP HER FROM DESTROYING IT.
THE DAM WAS HER NEXT TARGET.
OK, OK. I'M... I'M SORRY.
WHY DID YOU LOVE THIS WOMAN?
BECAUSE THROUGH IT ALL
I KNEW IT REALLY WASN'T HER.
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO MARY,
WHAT HAPPENED TO PAM
WASN'T A FAIR FIGHT.
I APPRECIATE THE SYMBOLISM,
BUT TECHNICALLY,
YOU JUST KILLED A TULIP.
YOU GOING SOMEWHERE?
YES, I AM.
THE QUESTION IS DO I PACK
ONE TOOTHBRUSH OR TWO?
GUYS AT THE PRECINCT
MENTIONED SOMETHING
ABOUT A BREAK-IN AT
GOTHAM DAM LAST NIGHT.
YOU WOULDN'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THAT, WOULD YOU?
I HAVEN'T BEEN
STUDYING MY ASS OFF
FOR MY DETECTIVE'S EXAM
FOR NOTHING.
WHAT ARE YOU PLANNING
TO DO THERE?
YOU WANT THE TRUTH SO YOU
HAVE TO BREAK UP WITH ME
OR A LIE SO WE CAN
STAY TOGETHER?
DON'T DO THAT.
DON'T PUT THIS ON ME.
WHY NOT? YOU ALREADY KNOW
WHAT I WANT.
I WANT TO SAVE GOTHAM
FROM BECOMING
A TOXIC WASTE DUMP, AND
I'D LIKE YOU TO SUPPORT ME
WHILE I DO IT,
SO...
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
FOR YOU TO CHOOSE ONE...
YOUR CAUSE, FLOODING THE CITY,
WIPING FULL NEIGHBORHOODS
OFF THE MAP, OR ME.
ABOVE ALL ELSE, I WANT YOU.
BUT I NEED YOU TO TRUST THAT
I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING HERE.
WHAT IS THIS FOR?
FORGIVENESS.
OHH!
YOU THINK OF SOMETHING?
YOU GOOD?
HEY. GOT SOMETHING.
BRUCE WROTE THAT POISON
IVY WOULD HAVE TO BE KEPT
WHERE NO ONE WOULD LOOK FOR HER
BUT SOMEWHERE HE COULD
GET TO HER IF HE NEEDED.
SO CLOSE. HE WOULDN'T
HAVE BURIED HER ANYWHERE
NEAR THEIR USUAL HOT SPOTS...
DOCKS, SHIPYARDS, BACK ALLEYS.
NO. IT'D HAVE TO BE
DARK AND DRY,
NO WATER, NO LIGHT,
NO OTHER PLANT LIFE.
WATER WAS HIS BIGGEST CONCERN.
A SINGLE DROP COULD BE
ENOUGH TO REANIMATE HER.
GOTHAM CITY IS A DAMN ISLAND,
WHERE IT RAINS 300 DAYS A YEAR.
ARE YOU SURE HE DIDN'T
MAKE A DEAL WITH GCPD
FOR SOME KIND OF SPECIAL
PROTECTIVE CUSTODY?
WELL, SHE'S NOT AT BLACKGATE,
AND I CHECKED THE OFF-BOOKS
WING AT ARKHAM, TOO.
THERE HAS TO BE AN ANSWER
WE'RE NOT SEEING.
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT IF SHE'S HERE?
YOU SPEND YOUR WHOLE LIFE
IN SERVICE
TO LOGIC AND FORENSIC EVIDENCE,
AND THEN YOU KNOW
WHAT LOVE DOES.
IT MAKES YOU WANT TO SAY
THINGS LIKE,
"I KNOW SHE'S DOWN HERE.
I CAN FEEL HER."
IF SHE'S IN THERE, ARE YOU SURE
YOU WANT TO SEE HER LIKE THIS?
RYAN AND I CAN HANDLE IT.
THANKS, BUT I OWE IT TO HER
NOT TO RUN AWAY AND HIDE.
THIS HAS THE SCHEMATICS
FOR THE TUNNEL SYSTEM
BELOW THE BATCAVE.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHERE WE'RE
GONNA END UP,
SO MAKE SURE WE FIND
OUR WAY BACK.
HOW FAR DOWN DOES THIS GO?
EVEN CLOSER TO HELL
THAN YOUR OFFICE.
OK. I NEED TOTAL QUIET.
SORRY, GUYS. DAMN FRAUD
ALERT ON MY CREDIT CARD.
Y... SILENCING.
I THINK I GOT SOMETHING.
TRYING TO ISOLATE IT.
OK. I'M LOCKED IN.
I CAN HEAR IT CLEAR ENOUGH
TO TRACK THE SOURCE.
HEAR WHAT?
- PAM'S HEARTBEAT.
- OH, MY GOD.
- YOU HAVE THE DEVICE?
- YEAH.
THEN WE NEED TO MOVE.
WHATEVER MARY'S UP TO,
SHE DOESN'T STAY
IN ONE PLACE FOR LONG.
LUKE, WE THINK PAM'S SOMEWHERE
IN THE LOWER TUNNELS.
AH. THAT IS ACTUALLY BRILLIANT.
A LOT OF SOLID ROCK DOWN THERE,
SO WE MIGHT LOSE CONTACT.
KEEP MARY THERE.
HELP IS ON THE WAY.
LET'S GO.
SO I KEEP WONDERING TWO THINGS.
WHY ARE YOU HERE,
AND WHERE'S WILDER?
YOU'RE SERIOUSLY THINKING
ABOUT YOUR SISTER RIGHT NOW?
SO YOU EXPECT ME TO THINK THAT
I COULD STEAL HER COMPANY...
AND SHE'S JUST COOL WITH IT?
HMM. IT'S HONESTLY
KIND OF ANNOYING
HOW MUCH CLINGINESS RUNS
IN YOUR FAMILY.
YOU WANT TO KNOW WHY RYAN
ISN'T PAYING ATTENTION TO YOU?
IT'S BECAUSE SHE'S TOO
OBSESSED WITH FIXING ME.
YOU DON'T LOOK BROKEN TO ME.
LOOK.
LONG STORY SHORT,
I JUST WANT TO MOVE ON
WITH MY LIFE
WITH THE ONE PERSON LEFT
WHO UNDERSTANDS ME.
UNH.
BUT THEN I THOUGHT TO MYSELF
THIS MARQUIS GUY HAS
A LOT OF WEIRD BAGGAGE.
MAYBE HE WANTS TO TAKE
REVENGE ON RYAN ON MY BEHALF.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE IN MIND?
OOP. WELL, LOOK
WHO STOPPED TALKING.
UM, A LITTLE BONUS FOR YOU.
IT MIGHT HELP OPEN UP SOME
DOORS FOR YOU IN THE FUTURE.
HEH HEH HEH.
RYAN, ARE WE HOT OR COLD?
TELL ME WE'RE SCALDING
BECAUSE WE'RE ALMOST
AT THE END OF THE MAP.
WELL, IT'S GETTING LOUDER. I
JUST DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH FURTHER.
- AGH!
- BATWOMAN...
- MARY AND MARQUIS...
- LUKE?
LUKE, YOU COPY? DAMN.
OK. THERE'S SOMETHING
GOING ON WITH MARY UPSTAIRS.
WE'RE ALMOST OUT OF TIME.
GUYS!
TELL ME SHE HAD
A CHARMING PERSONALITY.
THAT'S THE DESICCATION.
THE SERUM LEECHES WATER
FROM THE CELLS.
INCLUDES SKIN AND TISSUE.
YOU WANT TO DO THIS TO MARY?
I'M TRYING TO PREVENT
A POISON IVY OUTBREAK
FROM WIPING OUT GOTHAM'S
BEST AND BRIGHTEST UPSTAIRS.
LOOK, RYAN. I WAS YOU ONCE.
I WANTED TO BELIEVE THAT THERE
WAS SOME MAGICAL SOLUTION
WHERE I SAVED
THE LOVE OF MY LIFE
WITHOUT HER HATING ME FOREVER.
THERE ISN'T.
MARY IS AT THE PARTY.
THE SERUM IS HERE.
IT'S TIME TO STEP UP.
ALL RIGHT. GOT IT.
HEY, LUKE. IF YOU CAN
HEAR ME, I'M HEADED UP.
- WE'RE COMING WITH YOU.
- STAY AND MAKE SURE
PAM DOESN'T WAKE UP.
I'LL CHECK IN ONCE MARY'S DOWN.
REMEMBER, NO WATER BREAKS,
AND IF YOU SO MUCH AS
HAVE TO SNEEZE, DON'T.
JUST IN CASE.
HEY. BATWOMAN, IF YOU COPY,
I LOST EYES ON MARY.
WHERE ARE YOU?
- DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE COMING.
- GET THE HELL OFF ME, MAN.
OH, I DON'T THINK YOU
SHOULD BE TALKING LIKE THAT.
YOU'RE NOT WEARING
THE RIGHT COSTUME.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
SEE, I JUST WONDER
WHERE YOU KEEP IT.
PLUG IT IN LIKE A TESLA CHARGER?
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS.
BUT I THINK YOU DO, BATWING.
SHE'D FORGIVE YOU.
YOU HAVE NO CLUE HOW MUCH
OF A FIGHTER SHE WAS.
I'M TALKING ABOUT PAM,
THE WOMAN YOU FELL IN LOVE WITH,
NOT POISON IVY.
FOR THE RECORD,
I TAKE HALF THE BLAME
FOR ALICE GOING FREE.
NOT THE WISEST MOVE ON MY PART.
WE'LL FIND HER. SHE'LL
SCREW UP EVENTUALLY,
PING A TRAFFIC CAM, ROB A BANK.
ALICE? MORE LIKE HOLD UP
A DOUGHNUT SHOP.
OH, MY GOD. THE FRAUD ALERT.
WHOEVER STOLE MY CARD,
THEY PURCHASED
A 3-TIER STRAWBERRY CHEESECAKE
AND A GRAPE SODA,
THEN HAD IT SENT
TO HER HOTEL ROOM.
AND YOU THINK IT WAS ALICE?
KNOWING HER, SHE WON'T
BE THERE MUCH LONGER.
I NEED TO GET HER BACK.
ARE YOU GOOD HERE?
DOESN'T LOOK LIKE SHE'S REANIMATING.
I'LL BE FINE.
BE CAREFUL.
SORRY, MA'AM. ELEVATORS
ARE TEMPORARILY DOWN.
ALL OF THEM? WHY?
JUST SOME HICCUP WITH THE
BUILDING COMPUTER SYSTEM.
WE'LL GET YOU
ON YOUR WAY SHORTLY.
OH, RYAN, WHEN WILL YOU GIVE UP?
THE STAIRS ARE BETTER
FOR MY CALVES ANYWAY.
TOOK YOU LONG ENOUGH.
CAKE?
I BELIEVE YOU GET 5% CASH BACK.
- YOU LURED ME HERE?
- LURED YOU?
LET'S NOT GET KINKY.
ALICE, WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
I MADE A JUICY DISCOVERY,
AND I'VE BEEN DYING TO TELL YOU,
BUT YOU'VE BEEN SO HARD
TO GET ALONE LATELY.
HONESTLY, I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
HAPPENED TO OUR FRIENDSHIP.
WE DON'T HAVE ONE, FOR STARTERS.
BESIDES THE POINT.
YOU HAVE BEEN SO KIND
TO HOUSE ME ON THAT PRISON
COT YOU CALL A PULL-OUT COUCH.
I JUST WANTED TO RETURN
THE FAVOR.
YOUR LITTLE LOVER
HAS BEEN PLAYING US.
- RENEE?
- SURE,
OR WHATEVER YOU CALL HER
UNDER THE SHEETS.
SINCE WHEN DO YOU DO ME FAVORS?
BECAUSE RE-NAY-NAY IS A LIAR,
AND SHE NEEDS TO PAY
FOR BEING A BAD ONE.
SAYS THE WORLD'S BIGGEST LIAR.
YOU KNOW, RENEE'S HUGE MISTAKE
WAS LEAVING ME ALONE
IN HER OFFICE.
DID SHE NOT THINK I WOULD
SNOOP EVERY NOOK AND CRANNY?
LEFT CABINET,
SECOND DRAWER DOWN.
SEE FOR YOURSELF.
I DON'T WANT TO HURT YOU, MARY.
THERE'S ANOTHER PROMISE BROKEN.
OH! WHAT IS THAT?
DO YOU EVEN KNOW?
BATMAN MADE IT
TO STOP POISON IVY.
WHEN, A DECADE AGO? DO YOU
EVEN KNOW THE HALF-LIFE
OF ITS CHEMICAL COMPOUND?
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT
THAT'LL DO TO ME, DO YOU?
YOU GAVE ME NO CHOICE.
HEY, BATWOMAN. HOLD UP.
YOU READY FOR ME
TO BLOW YOUR MIND?
HOW ABOUT WE KILL YOUR
TWO LITTLE SIDEKICKS
AT THE SAME TIME, HMM?
A LITTLE BROTHER-SISTER
BONDING ACTION?
COME ON!
IT WAS ME. I TOLD HIM
SO YOU DON'T HAVE TO PUT
US ALL THROUGH THAT
"I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT" PHASE.
MARY... HOW COULD YOU?
YOU GAVE ME NO CHOICE.
I ALWAYS WONDERED
WHY I WAS THE KID
THAT GOT CHOSE
ON THAT BUS THAT DAY.
A COUPLE DOZEN KIDS, SO WHY
WAS I THE ONE THAT GOT BUZZED?
EVERYONE SAYS
THE WORLD'S GONE MAD,
BUT I GET IT.
BATMAN HAD THE JOKER,
AND, BATWOMAN, YOU GOT ME.
TRUE OR FALSE, SIS...
YOU GOTTA TRUST DESTINY.
FALSE. WE MAKE
OUR OWN DESTINIES.
YOU WISH.
UNH!
I'VE BEEN IN THE BEDROOM TRYING
TO FINAGLE MY WAY
OUT OF SOPHIE'S HANDCUFFS,
AND YOU'VE BEEN IN HERE
DRINKING ALL THE DOM?
RYAN HAD ME BEAT.
SHE WAS ABOUT TO INJECT
ME WITH SOMETHING,
AND THEN SHE HESITATED.
WHATEVER SHE WAS ABOUT
TO DO TO ME SCARED HER.
DON'T TELL YOU'RE GETTING
THE CONSCIENCE TINGLES.
BEFORE I EVEN KNEW
WHAT WAS HAPPENING,
SHE USED THE SYRINGE ON MARQUIS.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT WAS
TO SAVE LUKE
OR PROTECT HER SECRET.
BUT ALL I KNOW IS
IN THAT MOMENT,
I WAS THE LEAST OF HER PROBLEMS.
SHE STILL UNDERESTIMATES YOU.
I KNOW IT'S SILLY,
BUT A PART OF ME
JUST WANTED HER TO
SEE ME AS POWERFUL.
DO YOU KNOW ALL THOSE LOONEY
TUNE DELUSIONS I'VE BEEN HAVING,
POSTCARDS FROM DAD,
IMAGINARY FRIENDS,
WALKING IN ON SOPHIE
IN THE SHOWER?
THAT LAST ONE HAPPENED.
OH.
ANYWAY, SINCE YOUR WHOLE
POISON MARY METAMORPHOSIS,
I HAVE YET TO HAVE
A SINGLE DELUSIONAL THOUGHT,
WHICH MEANS BABY-SITTING
YOU, MY DEAR,
HAS MADE ME LESS
OF A CRAZY PERSON,
AND IF THAT'S NOT POWERFUL,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IS.
I KNOW YOU CAN'T HEAR ME.
I KNOW YOU HATE ME...
BUT I AM SORRY.
I'VE BEEN SORRY
EVERY DAY I WAKE UP
TO A BADGE AND NOT TO YOU.
OH, MY GOD.
PAM.
PAM, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
PAM?
OH, MY GOD.
DESICCATION IS NOT PRETTY.
DO YOU THINK WE SHOULD
HOOK HIM UP TO FLUIDS?
NOT UNLESS YOU WANT HIM
TO WAKE UP.
HE KNOWS WHO WE ARE.
THE SECOND HE WAKES UP,
THE WHOLE WORLD WILL, TOO.
THAT'S A BIG, FAT IF
HE WAKES UP.
JADA JET, THIS IS BATWOMAN.
I HAVE YOUR SON.
IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A WAY
TO FIX HIS BRAIN,
I SUGGEST YOU FIND IT QUICK.
SOPHIE, HOW DO YOU HAVE
RECEPTION IN THE TUNNELS?
I'M NOT IN THE TUNNELS,
BUT YOU NEED TO GET THERE ASAP.
SOPHIE, WHERE'S RENEE?
YOU KNOW WHY YOU AND ALICE
HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO CROSS THE JOY BUZZER
OFF HER LIST?
RENEE HAS HAD IT
THIS ENTIRE TIME.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN SHE HAD IT?
I MEAN, SHE WAS NEVER
GONNA LET ALICE FREE.
SHE LIED, RYAN,
TO ALICE, TO YOU, TO ME.
SHE WAS HOLDING IT
OVER YOUR HEADS
TILL ONE OF YOU FOUND
WHAT SHE WANTED...
HER SOUL MATE PAMELA ISLEY.
GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD.