Previously on Batwoman...
I'm Poison Ivy.
I nearly killed someone
and I don't know why
or when this infection
is gonna make me transform again.
Marquis is sick.
There was an incident.
The Joker had this zapper
on his hand.
He pressed it
against my son's forehead
After that day,
he was different, dark.
Horrifying.
You figured out
sunlight was my trigger.
Dad! Help! Help me!
You dad's gone, Luke.
I took out your failsafe
What up, sis?
You ready to blow up
the Gotham business world?
Well, we gotta make up for skipping
that rebellious teen phase.
Guess this is what
it would have felt like.
Sneaking out of the house
under Jada's nose.
Yeah, but instead of smoking blunts
in the pool house...
we're playing in a corporate merger
behind her back.
A true family business.
So, how do you propose
we make this happen
if you don't think
Jada would ever go for it?
Come on, the thing that we gotta do
is propose a plan
that everyone gets knows
then use the element of surprise.
Whoa... What the hell is this?
Yo, what are you doing?
I'm sorry, Marquis.
What... what is going on?
Mom, I don't understand.
It's for your own good, baby.
-Take him.
-Yes, Ma'am.
You took care of your family
and now your family
will take care of you.
Tell me more
about this favor you need.
Leaves of three, stay away from me!
Gotham's botanical garden
was the sight
of some horticultural hijinks
that sources say
bear a striking resemblance
to those of Gotham supervillain
Poison Ivy.
The toxic troublemaker
otherwise known as Pamela Isley
hasn't been seen in over a decade.
But judging by the size of the vines
found at the scene...
authorities can't help but wonder
if there's some other root cause
or does Gotham
need to break out its calamine?
Mary is Poison Ivy?
Oh, that depends.
She's kind of got a Jekyll and Hyde
thing going on.
So nighttime, she's fine.
But when the sun comes out,
the sweet and loving Mary
that we know takes a backseat
to a vegetation-wielding
supervillain.
I'm guessing Mary
is what happened to your arm.
Yeah, she made her point very clear
that she doesn't want me suiting up.
She also tried to squeeze the life
out of Batwoman.
No one has seen her since.
Is there a way to cure her?
Not yet. But there will be.
There will? How exactly?
Jada has the best minds
at Jeturian on it.
I gave them a sample of Mary's blood.
They are trying
to synthesize an antidote.
Your mom doesn't really do altruism.
So what's in it for her?
How long before
we can begin the freezing process?
As soon as my techs can flush
his system out of any intoxicants
or other contraindications.
Placing a human in suspended
animation is uncharted territory.
We don't want to rush things.
Then that should give you time
to focus on our other project.
Where are we with that?
Well, no one has seen
a plant-based infection
like this since Swamp Thing.
But you can eradicate it.
We're synthesizing the antidote now.
I'm sorry
I didn't say anything before
but I couldn't say anything
until Marquis was in custody.
You didn't have to do this alone.
I could have helped you.
He's unstable and dangerous.
I couldn't risk put anybody else
in jeopardy.
I get it.
Well, I don't.
So your mom got what she wanted.
And you really just trust that she
is going deliver on a cure for Mary?
We don't have much choice.
Jada's people tested Mary's blood.
They believe the infection's doubling
every 12 hours.
At that rate, this may be
the last night she's still Mary.
Where is she now?
I've made a facial recognition sweep
of every camera in Gotham
but no phone signal,
no credit card activity.
You're still hoping that when
the sun goes down, she'll call us.
Is that a hit on Mary?
No. It's Alice.
Her tracker says that
she's breached her 15-mile perimeter.
So she is off leash
hauling ass out of Gotham.
Your roommate happened to tell you
where she was going this morning?
I didn't exactly go home last night.
Great. So Mary is in the wind
and now Alice is making a run for it.
You don't think Mary's with Alice,
do you?
Why are we in a motor home?
Oh, because we wrecked
our super sexy sports car
fleeing the GCPD.
Alice, what did you do?
Actually, it's not what I did.
But if you don't remember,
it's probably for the best.
What do you want to listen to?
It's your turn to change the station.
Alice, stop.
Fine.
But we were making really good time.
I need to call Ryan and Luke.
Where is my phone?
You threw it into the Gotham River
on our way out.
Your idea.
Besides, you might want to let Ry Ry
and her little sidekick
cool off a little bit.
They are bound to be sore.
Figuratively and the other way.
- Is this Luke's Batwing AI?
- Oh, yeah.
Apparently,
you just ripped it right off
and almost took his arm
along with it.
I sincerely hope
he's not left-handed.
But don't worry.
It's not nearly as bad
as what you did to Ryan.
Oh, God, I'm gonna be sick.
Well, you're in luck.
Our new ride has a toilet.
Trust me, sister,
it's nicer than the one in Arkham.
Ryan and Luke would never put me
in there.
Well, it's not like you gave them
much of a choice.
I mean, you did try to kill them.
And as for Renee Montoya
finding out about you...
let's just say that cactus
is out of the bag.
I'm gonna be a fugitive
for the rest of my life.
No.
Just until you learn
to control your powers.
And I am happy to keep you safe
until then.
Just out of the kindness
of your heart?
Funny you should mention my heart,
actually.
Currently I have thousands
of creepy nanobots
running through my bloodstream
sending out annoying
little tracking signals.
And if they can find me, well...
they can find you.
Though, you wouldn't happen
to know a doctor
who could do a little
blood transfusion, would you?
But then you go free.
Sometimes you need
to pick your poison, dear.
Who do you trust more right now?
Your friends
who will surely lock you away...
or your sister
who is trying to keep you free?
What's your type?
Tall, dark, and brooding.
Your blood type?
O-negative.
You're about half a mile from Alice.
West on I-15.
That's weird.
Sorry. Signal's glitchy.
Let me widen out,
see if I can get a better look.
Uh-oh.
Not liking that sound
of that "Uh-oh."
Talk to me, Luke. What's going on?
Actually, I have another tracker
going east now.
How the hell is she
going east and west?
Oh, wait.
Now, I have one going north.
I've got Alices popping up
all over the map.
What the hell is going on?
Only one way to find out.
Batwoman. What did I do?
I'm a big fan.
- Please don't hurt me.
- Open the trunk.
No sign of Alice or Mary.
Okay, well I got
about 20 of them here.
They're scattering
in all different directions.
I don't get it.
I do.
Alice knows we're tracking
the nanobots in her blood
so she's been spilling it
on vehicles
heading in every direction
on the map.
And I know why Mary
hasn't called us yet.
She's with Alice.
And how was the hospital?
Not nearly as secure as it should be.
I got IV tubing, butterfly needles,
blood collection bags, but no blood.
At least that was locked away.
And yet only one iced caramel latte
that doesn't look big enough
to share.
I need the caffeine, okay?
Being two people is exhausting.
Before you call me a sucky fugitive,
I paid in cash
and I didn't use my real name.
Oh, okay. Good work, "Daphne."
Now I just need to find a donor.
Honestly, I'm not picky.
Actually, picky is exactly
what you need to be.
You're O-negative,
which means you're a universal donor
but you can only receive O-neg blood.
So how do we find
this special someone?
Hey.
You know what women find
so attractive in a guy?
It's not muscles,
or a big bank account, it's...
O-negative blood.
Big turn-on.
Shall we do a little checksie?
I'm good.
I don't know
what the hell's going on here
but you two are freaking out
our customers
with your vampire kink
or whatever it is you're into.
You gotta take it out of here now.
I'm sorry.
You're kicking us out of this place?
Simply because
we're trying to educate people
on the importance
of knowing their blood type?
You know what, miss?
You're completely right.
I am so sorry.
Stay as long as you want.
That was weird.
Oh, Mare-Bear.
It's about to get a lot weirder.
I think someone's mind-control
pheromones just kicked in.
How is that possible?
It's night
and I'm definitely still myself.
Well, get ready for the makeover
of a lifetime.
Because this may just be step one
of your blend
into full Poison Mary.
You don't believe me?
Take another stab at it.
Hey, can we get a bunch of shots
on the house?
You got it.
See?
People actually listen to this Mary
and she gets free stuff.
I think I'm gonna like her.
I just stole from a small business
and I don't even feel bad about it.
Welcome to the dark side.
Luke, we don't know how much longer
Mary's gonna be Mary.
You gotta get a line
on which tracker's the right one.
Blood cells can live outside the body
before for up to 4 to 6 hours.
When the blood cells die off,
the nanobots will shut down.
That's the plan?
Literally wait for blood to dry?
Hopefully it'll be by sun-up
so we can get to Mary
before it's too late.
Hey, not to add to our problems
but if she goes
full-blown Poison Ivy...
the mayor has authorized
extreme measures.
At the time, I didn't realize
they were talking about Mary.
Who's "they?"
Renee Montoya.
When did she tell you this?
So she's the reason
you didn't go home last night?
You were with her?
Didn't realize I needed
your permission.
To sleep with a woman
blackmailing me?
Threatening me with prison?
No, of course not.
I'm so happy you two
found each other.
All right. Just got word
from Jeturian, the cure is ready.
Copy.
Let's go.
Mama...
My hands sting.
Why are you doing this?
You know why, baby.
Ever since the Joker
pressed that buzzer to your head,
you haven't been the same.
That wasn't my fault.
I know.
And I need to fix you
before someone who doesn't understand
that tries to put you away for good.
Mama, I'm sorry.
For everything.
I love you.
I love you so much.
Just trust me on this.
Haven't I always taken care of you?
When you wake up...
you're gonna be my Marquis again.
Back off.
Do you want to be responsible
for killing Jada Jett?
I will kill her.
Marquis, what are you doing?
Doing what you taught me.
Taking initiative.
What the hell happened?
Marquis. He escaped.
Oh, my God.
Here, take it easy,
don't try to get up.
I thought Marquis was on ice?
We... we failed.
Where could he be now?
Ryan.
He went looking for you.
Nice sling.
Makes you look tough.
Is Ryan around?
I don't know where she is.
How did you get in?
I told the staff at the front desk
Ryan and I were blood.
Eighteen-karat gold nib.
Satin lacquer finish. Pricey.
- And hefty too.
- Can you put that down?
That's a gift from my dad.
Should've figured.
Now Lucius Fox always had
the best taste.
You know, your old man
used to come by our place some time
for my mom's famous
Moscow Mule nights.
Yeah. We'd shoot hoops
in the driveway sometimes.
Good man.
Dude, give me the pen.
No.
Is there a problem, Mr. Fox?
You called security on me?
Yeah, you don't need to be here
right now.
All right. Relax.
Luke and I were just chilling
while I wait for my sister.
You may know her as your boss.
Please escort Mr. Jet out.
Here's your pen.
Oh, that was a good shot.
You're quick.
I wasn't even warmed up yet.
Don't lie to yourself.
You wouldn't beat me
with two good hands.
You ready to wave the white flag?
Goodnight.
You're so awesome
to check my blood type.
But why are you checking
my blood type?
Because it's important to know.
I mean, imagine if you were in
a near-fatal accident.
You wouldn't want to run the risk
of being given the wrong blood.
Plus, how else would I be able
to find out if we're compatible?
Oh, okay. That makes sense.
It's AB negative.
That's not gonna cut it.
But that's a very rare blood type,
high in demand.
You should really consider donating
your plasma.
I'll go find a place to donate now.
Mary, this is Jason.
Jason and I have just been talking
about how hard it is
to meet people "organically"
nowadays.
Jason has no piercings, no tattoos
and he's never been to a country
where you can get Malaria.
Plus bonus, he's a Gemini.
You said there would be wings.
That's bad for your cholesterol.
Place your hand right here.
Now I want wings.
O-neg. We have a winner.
What did I win?
You get to donate two...
three pints of your blood
for a very good cause.
I'm gonna have to cut you off now.
Dr. Tuva didn't have a subject
to test the antidote on
but she's confident it will work.
Well, that makes one of us.
I just hope there's still time
to save Mary.
I know you don't trust me.
I've made a lot of mistakes.
But I always keep my promises.
It should be in here.
Marquis.
What have you done?
Luke.
Chill.
He's alive. I checked.
Your guard's another story.
Your fight is with me.
I'm the one who betrayed you.
I get why you'd be upset.
I know how awful that must have felt
to have your sister turn against you.
- What's so funny?
- You.
You thought I was wounded?
You think I'm all torn up inside?
Sad face because my long-lost sister
stabbed me in the back?
Marquis.
You don't have to pretend
you're not hurt.
Ryan, what, you don't get it?
This is me finally not pretending.
I can't believe you bought in
to the whole "sibling bonding" crap.
You know how hard it was for me
to keep a straight face?
Me and you against the world, sis.
So desperate to connect
with the family that didn't want you.
See, I would've thought that years
in the group home
would've toughened you up.
But you still fell for it.
Wait.
The look on your face right now,
it makes it all worth it.
Hold on. I'll take a picture.
- Use this as my background.
- You're sick.
Not as sick as your friend.
Yeah, Mom filled me in
on your little deal
before she blacked out.
Not off the red wine this time.
I don't even know what this stuff is,
but being that would have sold out
your own brother for it,
I'm sure it's important.
And considering that Mom's team
had a sunrise deadline, I'd say
it's pretty time sensitive, right?
Okay. Obviously you have a price.
So let's get to the part
where you tell me what it is
since the clock is ticking.
All business.
Yeah, me too.
And what I want is...
your autograph.
On a resignation letter of you
stepping down as CEO
of Wayne Enterprises.
I also want all your stock options.
You're trying to wage
a hostile takeover.
Yeah, and you're gonna help me.
If you wanna help your friend
in a timely fashion
and I'd say you got about
an hour until sunrise.
Do you need a pen?
I really wish I would've gotten
the chance to know the real you.
Before the Joker destroyed you.
See?
That's the thing.
If the Joker was so horrible...
why was he the only one
in this damn city
who looked like he was having
any fun?
Thanks.
Luke, I need a direction.
I'm all dressed up
with nowhere to go.
Good news, bad news.
Bad news first.
Okay.
Mary hasn't used her credit cards
and shockingly hasn't posted
on Insta.
So I don't have a bearing
to give you.
And we only have 42 minutes
until sunrise.
Okay. You better hit me
with the good news.
Nineteen of our trackers are offline,
so we're down to four.
That's the good news?
Didn't say it was that good.
So you got a one-in-four chance
of picking the right one.
Okay.
Let me know if any of the trackers
blink out.
Look, I'm not a doctor.
And at Point Rock, my field dressings
were famously terrible.
I'm just trying to channel
what Mary would say here.
She'd tell me...
She'd tell me that things can't heal
unless you let them.
And she'd be right.
Just like she was about me
and the suit.
And just because armor can cover up
a wound...
doesn't mean that it's not
still there.
You know what I did
when she tried to help me?
I pushed her away.
Because I just assumed
that she'd always be there.
Well, I took my eyes off Alice
to spend the night with Renee.
So if you're having a guilt party...
make room for one more.
So that's how Alice got out?
You and Renee are a thing now?
We're not a thing.
We had a thing, which technically
didn't even last until breakfast
which says a lot, considering
she lives above a GC Jitters.
That's it.
Coffee. That's how we find Mary.
How?
She's not using her credit cards.
Yeah, but if there's one thing
that a sleep-deprived Mary Hamilton
cannot live without, it is coffee.
And...
Yeah, she used her rewards card
at a GC Jitters
outside the Metropolis two hours ago.
That's our Mary.
Leave no reward point behind.
Looks like you know her better
than you think.
Okay, so...
The nearest tracker
to that GC Jitters location is...
Brownsville Pub?
Enough O-neg for a whole human.
It is amazing what two people
with nary conscience
between them can pull off.
I hope this goes better
than my last transfusion.
Nocturna?
You were there?
Right.
You mean when you saved your own skin
by siccing that off-brand vampire
on to moi.
By luring her with the fact
that I had Desert Rose in my blood
which was only there
because you gave my mom
the choice between her or me
with only one cure between us.
Yeah, I remember.
We've come a long way, haven't we?
Yeah.
For so long, all I wanted is you
to be out of my life.
I should just stick an embolism
in your IV
and finally just be done with you.
Or, option B,
you could finish my oil change
and you will never have
to see me again.
Actually, that's what I'm afraid of.
Hard to believe, right?
You don't want to be alone.
I know the feeling.
But you won't be.
I'm gonna stay with you through
this whole Mary metamorphosis.
You'd be a lot easier to trust
if you weren't a serial killer.
A serial killer who hasn't left you,
doubted you, or ignored you.
Do you really wanna
be alone right now?
Or do you want the help from
the only family you have left?
- Marquis?
- Hi, mom.
- Where are you?
- Right behind you.
Made you look.
Why are you calling?
To tell you to turn
on the TV tomorrow.
9.00am sharp. Any channel.
Why?
Because, Mama,
I'm gonna make you so proud.
Bye-bye, little robo-narcs.
I got to get out of these later.
How are you feeling?
Like my donor
should take an Uber home.
Giraffes or elephants?
Elephants.
They have longer memories.
I know we weren't
each other's first choice
in the sister department,
but I'm...
I'm really glad you're here.
Kate would've never done this
for me.
Hard same.
Kate would've never
let me do anything.
At least,
you believed I was capable
of doing more than
what everyone else expects of me.
Well, I'm glad the new you
finally agrees that everyone sucks.
You know, the first sign of sprouts,
Kate would've locked you away
in Arkham.
Yeah.
Then. she would've felt
really bad about it
in her journal.
Police. You're in possession
of a stolen vehicle.
Exit with your hands up.
This would be a good time
to use those pheromone powers.
I can't do it through the door.
You wanna open up?
I don't.
Stop!
Oh, my God! Stop!
I think we hit him.
I think that's a reason
to keep going.
Thank God.
I think we missed him
with the wheels.
He probably has a concussion.
He needs a ride to the hospital.
I'm sure one will come along.
You don't need to be that person.
I can't just leave him.
Old you can't leave him.
Remember her?
The one who always put everyone
else's needs above her own
and never gets anything in return?
New you puts herself first
and leaves behind anyone
who tries to stop her.
Hobbies include
long walks on the beach
and not being incarcerated.
Sorry, old me. Let's get out of here.
We need to ditch the nano-bots.
- Punch it!
- Consider it punched.
How fast can this thing go?
Why'd you stop?
I didn't.
So close.
Mary, you're gonna be fine.
We have a cure.
A cure? How?
It's a long story,
but we are running out of time.
This is probably
the last night you're you.
But look,
this will stop the infection.
- You can be you again.
- The old you.
The one they can use,
the one they can ignore
until they need to trot her out
for "Bat Team, Assemble."
Do you know how we found you?
Luke knew you couldn't resist
collecting your damn
GC Jitters points.
That's what best friends
know about each other, Mary.
Look at me!
You were the first person
to believe in me.
Now I need you to do it again.
There they go.
Telling you how to think.
I don't want to end up in Arkham.
It doesn't have to be that way.
Promise?
What will you do to me
if I don't take the cure?
I would have to keep you confined
until we figure something out.
We can't just let you
hurt people.
That's what I thought.
What did you do to me?
Mary, I'm trying to save you.
Well, maybe I don't want to be saved.
This isn't you talking.
No. This is you not listening.
If you think that I'm not myself,
then you don't know me at all.
It's time I step out of your shadow
and into my own sunlight.
Where's Mary?
She's not Mary anymore.
She didn't want to be saved.
Well, we're not giving up on her.
You don't get it.
I think she's given up on us.
All of Gotham is rocked
by this stunning new development.
The surprise resignation
of CEO Ryan Wilder
has left Wayne Enterprises
vulnerable to a hostile takeover.
What this means
for this legendary pillar
of Gotham City is still a mystery.
But we are standing by here
at Wayne Tower
where we are told
the new CEO of Wayne Enterprises
will be making a statement shortly.
Now you know why the Batmobile's
parked at a meter.
News vans
completely blocking the garage.
You wouldn't have been able
to get in anyway.
Our security clearances
have been revoked.
We're completely shut out
of Wayne Tower.
What about the Batcave?
I barely had enough time to initiate
the lockdown but...
Yeah, the Batcave is sealed.
We're not getting back in there.
But we got the Batsuit,
the Batmobile and not much else.
I am so sorry, Luke.
I traded away the Wayne legacy
for nothing.
You did it for Mary.
That's not nothing.
Good morning, citizens of Gotham.
I am honored and proud
to introduce myself
as the new leader in business.
You see, as times are changing,
it is time that we see
the big money makers follow suit.
Now, I know this town sees me
as a bit of a serial entrepreneur
but as the new CEO
of Wayne Enterprises...
I promise you a front row seat
to the bleeding edge of the industry.
Where you'll not only see
inspiring innovation
from visionary thought leaders
but you'll see that we're gonna
have a whole lot more fun.
While I was hired to fill the coffers
of my shareholders...
my main mission is to put a smile
on everyone's face.
As many of you know I worked from...
I am so hungover.
Then again, I was practically
turned into the human version
of a Long Island iced tea last night.
I need hash browns
and a coffee, stat.
What could possibly be
taking you so long?
You know, as much
as I make it look effortless
it takes time to make bad
look this good.
My, how you have blossomed.
I think your diabolical debut
deserves more
than a roadside greasy spoon
I don't care what we do
or where we go.
As long as it's fun.
And now I call you to join me
at the peak of greatness.
Well, he certainly looks like fun.