Previously on Batwoman...
You're responsible
for everything she does.
Until you two have tracked down
every last one of those toxic toys
from Batman's trophy case.
Right now, a thousand nanobots
are swimming
through your bloodstream.
Sending out tracking beacons
to satellites as we speak.
If I'm reading this right,
the suit thought you were injured.
Which prompted
a system-wide shutdown
putting the suit in safe mode.
I thought you and I agreed
you'd stay out of my business.
This is personal.
Because I'm your daughter.
Bus driver! Wait!
Bus driver, wait...
Wait, you piece of...
I pay taxes.
I pay your salary, man!
Screw you!
Yo. Wanna see something awesome?
Taylor, check this out.
T, look. I found it catching frogs
under Loeb Bridge.
I'm about to unlock a pet.
- Taylor, come on.
- Evan, chill.
Tell them I'm gonna be late.
I'm sorry. It's not my...
You gotta be kidding me.
I love this fricking town.
Gotham officials have no comment
on how a tank of liquid nitrogen
ended up
in the hands of schoolchildren
and caused this bus to freeze.
Gotham officials
are linking the freezing agent
to Mr. Victor Fries
the deceased cryobiologist
Gotham remembers
as one of Batman's coldest enemies.
Ms. Wilder is here for your meeting,
Ms. Jet.
Officials are asking
anyone with information
as to where the freeze serum
came from
to call the GCPD.
That's why I take the subway.
I'm sorry we didn't get a chance
to finish our conversation
last night.
I have to admit...
I never planned on meeting you.
It's a lot to process.
I see you've risen
above your circumstances
to get your degree.
Climb the corporate ladder,
become the acting CEO of Wayne.
You've turned yourself
into a rather remarkable
young woman, Ryan.
Thank you.
Look...
I didn't come here
to blame you for anything.
You know, whatever your situation was
at the time
if you were young or scared
or if I was unplanned,
unwanted, whatever.
No judgment.
I just wanted you to know
that it's all good.
I turned out okay.
Ryan, in an effort to respect
your time and mine
I will try to make this
as simple as possible.
I'm not interested
in having a relationship
with you.
Now, if you don't mind
I have a meeting
I need to prepare for.
Wait... Why have me
and then cover it up?
Adam, will you let Bonnie know
that I'm on my way?
You paid a doctor two million dollars
to fake your name
on my birth certificate
and then made it look like you died
so I never came looking for you.
What were you afraid of?
Sometimes, it's better
to stop asking questions.
So you invited me here
just to show me the door?
If you continue to try to have
anything to do with my family
I will personally see to it
that you and Wayne Enterprises
will come to severely regret
that decision.
I always wondered
who my birth mother was.
Now I know.
Someone not worth my time.
I'm glad we're on the same page.
I missed it? Damn.
See, this is what I get
for second-guessing my kicks.
I went deep vault for you, Wilder.
Worth it?
I actually used to have those
in blue.
There you go. Worth it.
See, we're connecting already.
Marquis,
I thought you were on your way
to Metropolis Magazine's
influencer party tonight?
I was, then I heard
you were sitting down
with a new young CEO without me
and I figured
there was a scheduling oversight
so I bounced.
I'm sorry. Who are you?
You're new new.
That's cool.
I won't take any offense.
I'm Jeturian Industries'
executive vice president.
Marquis Jet.
Also known as my son.
You were very clear about
knowing the absolute minimum.
You weren't even sure
if you wanted to get to know Jada.
So knowing she had another kid,
it would've just complicated it more.
A kid she kept
while she gave me away.
Was he cool at least?
I have no idea.
Jada kicked me out of there so fast
I didn't even to get
my parking validated.
This is exactly why I wanted
to keep that door closed.
- So what now?
- You didn't hear?
Mr. Freeze's liquid nitrogen can
got in the hands
of a bunch of eighth graders.
I need to find it.
I mean, about your mom.
What can I do?
What do you need?
You poor thing.
I'm so sorry, Ryan.
Thanks.
It sucks, but I'll be fine.
Okay, first, how dare she.
And second, how did you even know
she was still alive?
Okay, everyone was like
"Boo-hoo,
evil Alice killed Ryan's mom."
As if it wasn't bad enough.
And now against all odds
I miraculously provide her
with another one
and you guys
are just bitching and moaning...
Can I get some water?
Please, someone.
Okay, please tell me you have
some info on this freeze stuff.
So the canister itself is a compact.
It's custom-built vacuum flask
that makes its contents,
aka the freeze stuff
more concentrated
and seemingly less dangerous
than it is.
Little goes a long way.
So the kid likely found it
near the Gotham River
and thought
it was a harmless dry-ice gun.
All right,
I'm really not feeling well.
I think it's all these
tracking nanobots inside me.
My skin, it...
feels like spiders
are running through my veins.
Okay, that's not a thing.
Wayne Tech uses nanobot injectables
in their research all the time.
Are you calling in sick?
Is that what this is?
Montoya wants us to work together.
My team gets a beat
on a Batman trophy
and then you use
your creepy-ass brain
to help us figure out where it is.
And I would love nothing more, truly
than to talk about
an errant can of liquid nitrogen
but I am finding it very difficult
to focus through my pain.
And I would hate
Ms. Montoya to think
that our little arrangement
didn't work
on account of me
being in a hostile work environment.
Oh, my goodness.
What did I do to deserve this?
You know, it's probably
not the worst thing
if we give Alice the sick day.
Why does she get a day off?
Because I know where the canister is.
Plus, I doubt that you want
one of Gotham's Most Wanted with you
breaking into the GCPD.
- I'm in.
- Cool.
I can only keep the cameras dark
for five minutes, so start looking.
You sure it's here?
Logs say it was tagged and filed
at 10.07am this morning.
No record of anyone removing it.
I think I know why Batman kept
his own evidence locker.
What is this?
What did you do?
I found it, Nora.
We can finally finish
what Victor started.
You stole Victor's freeze tank?
Nora Fries.
You are gonna tell me
how you were frozen for 20 years...
and lived to talk about it.
I was able to compare
entry and exit footage
from the time of the theft
and track down who broke
into the evidence room first.
Are you sure about that?
Dee works
at the GCPD processing desk.
She's one of the few people
who has access to the evidence room's
secure back area.
Dee also called in sick today
and this lady has never
called in sick once in 20 years.
Okay, but...
All the items in the evidence room?
There has to be something
easier to fence.
Which is what I thought.
Why would anyone risk everything
for this stuff
apart from the guy who invented it?
Wait, you mean the Mr. Freeze dude?
- I thought he was dead.
- Victor Fries. He is.
Brilliant cryobiologist.
Half a dozen doctorates.
Still insisted on being called
Mr. Freeze.
But then again, Captain Cold
wasn't really a captain, so...
Who's that?
Yes.
That is Nora Fries
in an Arkham intake photo
taken three years ago.
So Nora was diagnosed
with the MacGregor's syndrome
a progressive lung disease
that at the time of her diagnosis
had no cure.
So Victor created
a unique liquid nitrogen formula
to supply a cryochamber
that kept her in stasis
until a cure could be found.
And he died before it happened.
Well, eventually
her cryochamber ran out of Victor's
liquid nitrogen cocktail.
So when she thawed
Nora learned that doctors found
a cure for MacGregor's.
So they administered it
but she was so disoriented
by the 20-year-time gap
that officials sent her to Arkham.
She escaped in a breakout
three years ago
and has been MIA ever since.
So what's the connection?
Dee Smithy is Nora Fries's sister.
Send me the address.
I'll fire up the Batmobile.
Okay.
Who's bouncing a basketball
off of Bruce Wayne's shelf
of first editions?
That would be my brother.
Girl's got reflexes. You play?
Yeah, in all my spare time.
What are you doing here?
You free for a drink later?
Jada didn't tell you about me.
Tell me what, Wilder?
She made it very clear
she wanted nothing to do
with Wayne Enterprises
and that
l have nothing to do with her.
You ruffled some feathers.
What did you do?
Because normally,
she eats the rags-to-riches stuff up.
Reminds her of herself.
So you think you know my story.
Twenty-seven.
Raised in the system,
stint at Blackgate
and now acting CEO of Wayne.
Oh, and you're my sister.
She told you that?
She didn't have to.
How did you figure this out?
Oh, nannies talk.
Like mine did when moms disappeared
for nine months straight.
Heard about it as a kid years later
while her and my old man didn't speak
for a full summer after that.
So it was an affair.
Then we fast forward 27 years.
Here's some bad-ass chick
one year younger than me.
Shows up at the company,
throws my mom off her game
and has got her scheduling
all these secret meetings
while I'm supposed to be out of town.
Here you are.
The sister I never knew I had.
I would ask for a hug
but you look like
you could kick my ass, so...
Pretty sure
your mom might beat me to it.
Our mom.
I don't think you should be here.
But I already picked out my office
next to yours.
What are you talking about?
Because it's the corner.
Way better view, I mean...
I don't even know
why you're in this place.
It's so limited.
You wanna partner
with Wayne Enterprises?
Mom thinks that I'm in this
just for the PJs
and free concert tickets.
Which would mean
I'd be an honorary VP
until she's dead in her Loubies.
Unless I make my mark.
Show what I can do.
Same with you.
Why don't you show her what
she missed out on the last 30 years?
What do you say, sis?
Wanna join forces?
Show her what we got?
You said you'd think about it?
I couldn't exactly ask him
to wait in the lobby
while I followed the 20
on a missing freeze tank.
What's exactly is there
to think about?
What it might be like
to actually have a brother.
Okay, I get that.
But Jada Jet didn't earn her spot
on the Forbes 150
by making idle threats.
She literally promised to destroy
Wayne Enterprises.
Okay, okay. I'm in Dee's house.
We're late to the party.
Someone was here, and it got ugly.
- No sign of Dee or the freeze tank.
- What?
Or the roommate we didn't know about.
I think Nora's living here.
But I thought you said they found
the cure for MacGregor's syndrome.
They did.
According to Nora's medical records,
she received it years ago.
Okay, well, from the looks of it,
she's still sick.
Maybe it didn't take?
Maybe Dee wanted to put Nora
back in her cryochamber
to save her sister's life.
So who broke into the house?
Someone after the same thing?
I don't suppose you know
where one would find a cryochamber.
What do you know about Ace
Chemicals?
Only that no good thing
ever happened there.
And I'm sending you the address now.
Here. Everything you need to know
about cryogenics.
My brother-in-law
kept meticulous notes.
What's your problem?
Just learned
my sister was gonna put me on ice
and now I got a gun on my bad hip.
What do you think I'm gonna do, run?
These are the musings of a madman.
I can't read this.
You gotta show me how it works.
How on earth would we know
the first thing about that?
They didn't even offer science
to women when I was at university...
Show me or she dies.
BP and heart rate are totally normal.
98.6.
Glucose levels
are as average as they come.
Which are all common symptoms
of faking it.
You know, with care like this
it's amazing
you managed to save any lives.
There's nothing wrong with you,
Alice.
At least not physically.
I'm sorry.
I think my dangerously high fever
is interfering
with whatever you are hinting at.
The postcards from Dad?
You know, it's funny,
I was actually kind of jealous of you
when I thought that
he was writing to you and not to me.
And then when I found out
that it was just
you being totally delusional
it honestly was a relief.
Oh, I'm so glad my madness
has soothed your daddy issues.
Does what happen a lot?
Those delusions?
Just the once.
So this whole performative
"I'm sick" thing
isn't, I don't know,
a cry for help, maybe?
I learned a long time ago
that cries for help don't work.
Look...
I'm an official doctor now
so if you need actual help,
I have to give it to you.
So do you?
I see what's going on here.
You couldn't help Bat Boy
so now you're burdening me
with your savior complex.
Bat Boy?
Yeah. Luke.
It says in his files he's having
some unfortunate performance issues.
You went through my files?
Okay, that cabinet is locked.
I broke out of the Crows
with a fishing line.
Your Office Warehouse cabinet
didn't stand a chance.
Anyway, it's your fault
for taking forever to see me
and not giving me any magazines.
I assume that Batwoman knows
she's working
with an emotional ticking time bomb?
Batwoman doesn't break
into my file cabinet
because it's called
doctor-patient confidentiality.
Perfect. I'm not a doctor.
So what's the issue?
Now you're in the middle.
Oh, that's a dilemma.
Do you tell bossy pants Batwoman
that Luke's ignoring
his PTSD symptoms
or do you keep Luke's secret
because you love him?
I do not love Luke like that.
You have no idea
what you're talking about.
Sure.
But a little piece of advice.
And keep that to yourself.
Telling Ryan
will only fill you with resentment.
How do you figure?
Because she'll ignore you, Mary.
I'm sorry.
Do you not see your place
on this team?
I've been on it for less than a month
and it's already glaringly obvious
they don't see you
unless they need you.
Just like Daddy and just like Kate.
So if you want to go on liking them
it's probably best
to know your place.
Watch your six.
Got a read on some major firepower
in the south parking lot.
- I got eyes on three more inside.
- Copy that.
Be careful, Batwoman.
This is going to make my client
very happy.
- Until he realizes it doesn't work.
- Can it, Nor.
You think we're walking out of here?
We've seen their faces.
What do you mean it doesn't work?
It works fine.
Just a little dust,
a few disinfectant wipes...
The chamber works.
It'll freeze you solid
but you'd die of hypothermia
eventually.
Well, then what's the point
of this stuff?
Constant exposure to the freeze serum
will stop time
and keep you from aging.
Coming out of it
is a whole other story.
Look, my husband was brilliant.
But he didn't realize
that once I was released
from the chamber and thawed
time would catch up.
Three years ago, I came out
of that thing a 34-year-old.
And look at me now.
At this rate,
I'll be 122 by Christmas.
But your sister was about
to lock you back inside of it.
The only way
to stop my sister from dying
is to put her back on ice
till I can find a way
to slow the aging.
That's some dedication.
Well, if what she's saying is true,
this is going to be a major problem.
Add me to that list.
Get her out of here.
- Can you walk?
- Better than her.
Okay. There's a clinic
on Rucka and Bennett.
It's not far.
They'll take care of you.
- I can't leave Dee.
- I'll find her.
A gun? Could you be more basic?
Come on. Let's do this.
Come on!
All right,
let's see this thing in action.
My client wants to know how it works
without wasting product.
But that's the whole point
of Victor's liquid nitrogen.
The formula is what keeps her alive.
Turning on the machine without it
will just blast her with cold air.
She'll die from hypothermia.
Does it look like I care?
I'm not killing Batwoman.
How long do you think it's gonna take
for my driver to find your sister
just hobbling down Rucka Street
and make her roadkill?
Turn it on or your sister dies.
If Batwoman doesn't die...
you do.
Take her to the car.
Batwoman to Batcave.
Gonna need a little help.
Whoa, talk to me. What is happening?
They trapped me in the cryochamber.
- What?
- Get me the hell out of here.
I'm calling up your biometrics.
Your core body temperature's
dropping like crazy.
Yeah, I'm pretty aware of that.
Okay...
Access the suit's temp regulator.
Yeah.
Oh, boy.
Seriously?
You couldn't keep that to yourself?
The regulator must've frozen up.
You have ten minutes
before a full-blown hypothermia.
You need to stay awake, okay?
Luke...
You need to suit up.
Help Dee.
They took her somewhere.
What? No!
I gotta keep you from passing out.
I am okay.
Go find her.
- If you pass out, it's over, Ryan.
- I won't.
Okay?
Go find her.
I promised...
I promised Nora
I would protect her sister.
Please don't let me die a liar.
Any word from Dee?
Batwoman's on it.
She won't let anything happen
to your sister.
Have you considered cataract surgery?
That'd be a bit like
cleaning the windows
on the Hindenburg.
Dr. Hamilton,
I was 34 for two decades.
I got out
and started aging double time.
Life's catching up to me.
Why stand in the way?
I thought that's what you wanted.
To literally
stand in the way of time.
I have an idea.
Let's talk about what I want.
What the hell are you doing?
Get these nanobots out of me now!
You know I can't do that.
Because that's the only thing
preventing you
from escaping Gotham entirely.
I wonder why I want them gone.
Get them out!
- Batwoman would kill me.
- And I will kill Nora.
Do you not understand
cause and effect?
- How do you have an MD?
- Let her.
- What?
I am so sick of people
sacrificing their lives for me.
My husband, my sister.
The research, the lost years,
the desperation.
For what?
So I can be trapped all over again?
So you want me to kill you?
Could you be a worse hostage?
What is wrong with you?
I literally just let her go.
I was being nice to you.
Nice?
You think I want nice?
You think I want
this stupid arrangement with Batwoman
who I can't even stand
and Little Miss Judgie Two Shoes
being nice?
It's no wonder
I'm losing my freaking mind.
I am so sorry about that.
Believe it or not, she is my sister.
You certainly fight like it.
But I gotta say, I understand her.
You understand the woman
who just had you at knifepoint?
I follow the news.
She's been trapped her whole life.
And now she wants her freedom.
Does your sister know that
that's what you want?
Dee's wasted too many years
of her life trying to fix me.
I love her too much
to tell her the truth.
Batcave to Batwoman.
Sophie?
Batwing's en route. Are you good?
I'm fading.
I just wanna sleep.
Yeah, that's the hypothermia talking.
You know, it's awfully convincing.
Yeah, but you can beat it.
But you gotta stay awake.
If you sleep, you die.
I can't...
I can't stay awake.
Then maybe this is a good time
to tell you I'm mad at you.
Me?
What'd I do?
Where do we stand? You and me.
Because you were willing to have me
do all the dirty work
to find your mom
but when it came to sharing
how you actually felt about her
you went straight to the Bat Team.
Hang on.
Are you telling me...
that I hurt your feelings?
I'm telling you, you don't know me.
At all.
You think you do.
You have no idea.
Okay. Captive audience here.
What should I...
What should I know about...
Batwoman, don't fall asleep on me.
Batwoman?
Ryan! Ryan, wake up!
Hey, hey. I got you. You're okay.
Batwoman, are you good? Batwing?
Someone talk to me.
Check in!
Yeah, yeah, she's okay, she's okay.
She's conscious.
I got her.
Traffic cams found us two vehicles
matching the SUVs from Ace.
Northbound, about six miles out.
Got a glimpse of Dee in the back.
So she's alive. Thank God.
Clever.
- Me?
- Sophie.
Me?
The way you kept me
from nodding off back there.
You're clever.
Which means you're right.
There was something
I didn't know about you.
I will take that as a thank you.
Are you flirting with Sophie
right now?
What? No.
What are you doing?
I know what flirting is.
What was that?
I am not flirting with Sophie.
Guys. Comms. On.
They just turned
onto the Tricorner Bridge.
Got them.
Hold this.
We're good!
We lost them.
Not to state the obvious
but you do see that impassable gap
in the bridge, correct?
I need a copy on the chunk of bridge
missing at your twelve o'clock.
Control freak.
Add that to the list too.
Batwoman,
what the hell are you doing?
It's working.
Gun it! Now!
Yeah!
That was bad ass.
You gotta admit. That was bad ass.
It was interesting.
Interesting?
Woman, you are hard to please.
Hurry up! She's gaining!
Get out. Get out.
Let her go.
Let's hope Victor took good notes.
What the hell is happening to me?
Not much left
but Renee was willing
to cross it off her list.
Thanks for the having my back
back there.
Guess it's safe to say
you figured out the glitches
in your super suit.
You could say that.
It's because
he disabled the fail-safe.
His dad designed the suit
to react to Luke's physiology.
A surge in heart rate shuts it down.
That seems counterintuitive.
Because he's not supposed to wear it
until he's ready.
Mary. What are you doing?
I shouldn't have cleared you
for field duty.
I'm sorry.
I put your life and this team
in jeopardy.
You want to worry about the team?
Worry about the psychopath
who held Nora at knifepoint today.
Alice was having a temper tantrum.
You were having
a physiological reaction to stress.
Look, I'm the team doctor.
I know what I'm talking about.
I hear you, Mary.
And thank you.
But I wouldn't be standing here
if Batwing hadn't been with me
last night.
And what about next time?
That's a risk we both take.
No offense, Ryan.
But you don't have PTSD
from being shot.
I don't have PTSD.
Okay. Give it to me straight.
Are you up for this?
Absolutely.
Okay. Then keep an eye on it.
But until we get these weapons
off the street
I need Luke by my side.
I had to say something.
No, you didn't.
Thank you.
You don't sleep, do you?
He knows I'm his sister.
- How?
- He's smart and ambitious.
And incredibly reckless.
He wants to work together.
Behind Jada's back.
What do you want?
It's funny.
When it came to family,
I never allowed myself
to ask that question.
But then,
Alice ripped off the Band-Aid.
I'm...
If I'm being real?
I want a mom
who knows all my food allergies
and tells me my skirt's too short
and texts my girlfriend
about TV shows they like
and loves me unconditionally.
That's what I want. I want a mom.
It's her loss, Ryan.
Yeah.
Well, Jada is one of the most
connected people in Gotham.
Which means making her my enemy
puts everyone I care about at risk.
So as tempting as it is
to have a brother...
I gotta put the team first.
There's a bronchodilator
to help with the breathing
and meds to help with the pain.
Should be enough to manage the pain
these next few days.
Are you sure
you wanna risk being out?
GCPD's probably out hunting for us
as we speak.
Batwoman took care of it.
Neither one of you
have anything to worry about.
Thank you, Dr. Hamilton.
Victor and I had our first date
in this park.
Are you sure you're not tired?
We can go home.
Dee, I want to breathe in
the fresh air
with whatever lungs I have left.
And then I want to let it all go.
You're giving up?
I've been dying my whole life, Dee.
Instead of trying to stop time,
this once
what do you say we enjoy
the precious moments we have left?