Previously on Batwoman.
Ever since the Joker
pressed that buzzer to your head
you haven't been the same.
And I need to fix you.
What are you doing?
Taking initiative.
How about we kill
your two little sidekicks
at the same time?
Do you think
we should hook him up to fluids?
Unless you want him to wake up.
Another jolt would reawaken
his empathy.
But I have spent millions
looking for the buzzer
but no one's seen it.
Ten years, and, suddenly,
it's like yesterday.
What were you thinking would happen
when you freed me?
I wasn't. I got wrapped up
in the moment seeing you.
I thought the water would revive me.
I need to get my strength back.
Hello?
- Get away from me!
- Whoa, no!
Oh, little sister.
What have you done?
Maybe that'll get you
out of your head.
You found me.
No.
What the...
What is happening?
This is so not me.
You underestimate yourself, Mary.
Just like your friends always have.
What the hell is going on?
I need you to...
Hello.
I'm Dr. Hamilton.
Do you know who I am?
Of course. Harold Marlowe,
CEO of Gotham United Healthcare.
We didn't just kidnap a rando.
This was a focused,
specific abduction...
Get to the point. Too many words
gets a little mustache-twirly.
Here's the thing, Harry.
I've treated tons of patients.
Single moms, students, the unhoused.
You know what they all have
in common?
Please, please.
They all have claims denied by you.
Please.
Perhaps if you spent
a little more time in nature
you might have the chance
to put yourself in their shoes.
Imagine you're the dad of a kid
whose treatment isn't covered
so you work two extra jobs.
Your kid...
gets sicker and sicker.
You get poorer and poorer.
Please, please.
You lose your home
you're living in your car
you're drowning
in a lifetime of debt.
And, suddenly, just having a sick kid
seems like a day off.
Damn, that felt good.
That was epic. Did you rehearse that?
Oh, I've been dealing
with the horrors
of the Gotham healthcare system
for a while now.
But I think that
you just unlocked something.
- You found your calling, doc.
- I mean, I get it now.
Justice. Using this gift
to level the playing field.
Now, the press
is gonna label you a villain.
They're gonna call you unhinged
and use way too many puns.
But if you just do what feels right
they can't stop you.
Yeah.
Pam.
Your nose. It's happening again.
I didn't even do the heavy lifting.
Here.
I can take it.
Go ahead.
Thank you, Mary.
No problem.
You okay?
I'm fine.
Let's go.
Yeah, hi. We have a problem.
Pamela Isley beckoned Mary
all the way from Metropolis?
Why didn't you stop her?
Believe me, I tried.
Mary mind-roofied me.
And while a deep betrayal
at the time
if I'm being honest
I haven't slept that well
since I torched Mabel Cartwright.
Hold up. Mary pheromone'd you?
I thought you two were buds?
And I thought
you were working out of Renee's
but I got to say, I'm loving
this whole commuter-coffee shop vibe
you've got going on.
Why should we trust anything you say?
Because I'm in a gay bar
when I'm supposed to be in Santorini.
So you do the math.
Look, we couldn't stop Mary.
We got our asses kicked by the OG.
So how do you suppose that we stop
two Poison Ivys at the same time?
Easy.
You wanna kill a plant,
you take away its sunshine.
Not easy, seeing as though none of us
can actually control the weather.
She means Renee.
We go after Pam's weakness.
You're gonna wanna get on that today.
ASAP.
Like, ten minutes ago.
Your deal with Renee for your freedom
was a scam
which means you're a wanted criminal.
You wouldn't risk coming back here
unless there was something deeper
going on.
So, what is it?
Me?
Deep?
There's no need for insults.
Besides
we're running out of time.
Not gonna lie, what you said
to that insurance sleaze
really hit home.
Didn't take you
for a paying-your-premiums type.
Well, my little brother
had really bad asthma growing up
and we didn't have a lot of money
so our mom got super into plants,
herbal remedies.
A few years after my brother got sick
we learned that
our drinking water had been poisoned
by the factory up the hill.
Doctors said it was a miracle
we weren't all in the hospital.
My brother didn't make it
to his 13th birthday.
I thought Renee said
she'd pick us up at the road.
She did.
Hey, I got the tickets.
I'm about 20 minutes away
so pack up,
I'll swing by to grab you.
Where are we packing for?
Miss us?
Apparently not, since she's leaving
without saying goodbye.
What is this?
Oh, this is us
catching you mid-betrayal
and reminding you
we have a binding contract, Renee.
You know what that is?
Gotham Dam.
Toured it
on a fourth grade field trip.
Let me guess.
You learned that it supplies power
to over half the industry in Gotham
and saves the city money.
Did they also tell you
that it's responsible
for the extinction
of an entire species of fish?
Dried out riverbeds?
Eroded farmlands?
To be honest,
I wasn't really paying attention.
No one is.
And then we wake up in 50 years
and our planet is dead
because we killed it.
What are we doing here?
I wanted to show you
my passion project.
This dam feeds
into Gotham's industrial district.
The factory that killed your brother.
One of them.
But there are dozens more
doing the exact same thing.
Finding loopholes in regulations,
no consequences.
Mary.
I brought you here
because I was hoping
you would help me help Mother Nature
drown Gotham's industry in her tears.
Oh, are those too tight?
I'm not sure what you think
this will accomplish.
Well, for one, you're not getting
on a plane right now.
You're gonna tell us
where your girlfriend took Mary.
Like I said, betraying Pam
was the biggest mistake of my life.
I'm not doing it again.
It wasn't a mistake.
You said it yourself,
you saved hundreds of lives
by putting her away, and you know it.
It was the right move.
Keep me here as long as you want.
I'm sure the owners of this place
will find it great for business.
They are the owners of this place.
- Hey.
How did you know we were...
Luke called, thinking I could help.
Is that a problem?
No.
Okay, now that that's sorted
Soph, dear, can you fix this?
What is Sophie supposed to do?
Like you've never stolen
Sophie's cell phone
and read her private text messages?
- They've been intimate.
- Okay, this is ridiculous.
The only ridiculous part
is us thinking we could trust you.
When were you gonna tell everyone
that you have the joy buzzer
this whole time?
Oh, you really think I was gonna let
a psycho killer loose in the city
I spent my career protecting?
Now, I'm confused.
Are we talking about Alice or Pamela?
Let's cut to the chase.
You are gonna tell us
what Pam did with Mary
or this psycho killer's
gonna show you what she can do
with a lemon zester.
Trust me, I've done worse with less.
Hey, Batwoman, heads-up.
Someone just turned on
the Bat signal.
Hey.
Go ahead. Let me talk to Renee.
I know how to think like a cop.
We'll get Mary back.
I gotta go.
You're playing a dangerous game
taking a son from his mother.
I took him to stop the dangerous game
he was playing.
And here I thought
the city found you charming.
Where's the buzzer?
The Joker pressed
this god-forsaken thing
to my son's head
and turned him into a monster.
I've been told
that another buzz could cure him.
If there's a way
to make it work again, I'll find it.
If you think I'm handing this to you
without getting my son back
you're crazier than he is.
You don't get it.
If he wakes up before we figure out
how to make that thing work
you're the first one he goes after.
I'm safe.
My son and I have an arrangement.
Really?
Well, does that arrangement
trickle down to your employees?
The last time Marquis
was in your custody
it didn't go so well for them.
How do you know anything about that?
Your people talk more
than you'd like.
And here you thought
they all found you charming.
Give me the buzzer.
I'll find a way to make it work.
It's the only choice you have here.
If I give you this
I want my son back in exchange.
Fine.
By midnight.
Or we have a problem.
Terrifying, isn't it?
It's a small ocean.
That's what happens when
you redirect entire river systems.
What are we doing up here?
I have to unlock
the grates of the turbines
so we can get started.
But you'll flood
more than the industrial district.
You could wipe out half the city.
If I wanted Renee here,
I would have invited her.
I'm not trying to be a Renee-sayer
but unleashing this much water
on a major metropolitan city
- could kill a lot of people.
- Yes.
And by taking out those polluters,
we'll save so many more.
To say nothing of the environment.
I wanna help you, Pam.
Seriously, I owe you so much.
But I finally figured out what to do
with all of this energy, this power.
And I don't need to be drawing
the kind of heat that comes
with being the girl
who drowned the city.
I get it.
This isn't your fight.
I'm not gonna make you do something
that you don't wanna do.
Thank you.
But I still need your help.
Pam, you're hurting me.
Please.
Let me go.
Thank you, Mary. I mean that.
I could not have done this
without you.
Found her just lying here.
She's alive.
What the hell is she doing up here?
I'll call it in. Go search the place.
See if there's anybody else.
I don't get it, Renee.
I know you're smart
and I know you know what comes next.
Aiding and abetting
obstruction of justice,
stealing evidence.
Need I go on?
I'm curious, though.
If the roles were reversed
would Pamela be sitting here,
risking everything for you right now?
You're right. You think about that.
- Seriously?
What? 72 hours of this,
and she'll be singing like a canary.
Tell me you're having more luck
with the scanner.
Nothing out of the ordinary.
Hey, what was up with Ryan before?
When?
You know,
when she was weirdly surprised
that I didn't check in with her
before I invited you down here.
- She didn't tell you?
- Tell me what?
Doesn't matter.
Well, arguably,
it matters even more now.
3-6-5 en route with a priority one.
Approximately 25-year-old female.
Unconscious.
We're on Route 99 heading west,
about 18 miles out.
Copy, 3-6-5. We're ready receive.
Not sure if you wanna notify family,
but my partner recognized her
as Commander Jacob Kane's daughter.
Over.
Not-Batcave to Batwoman.
Jada gave me the buzzer.
And then, in return, she demanded
Marquis back by midnight.
- Or else...
- Or else what?
Knowing takes all the fun out of it.
But the last time she thought
I screwed her over
she tanked Wayne
and we lost the company.
Okay, as much as I love reminiscing,
Mary was just found unconscious.
- Wait, is she okay?
- That's all I got.
She's en route to Gotham General.
G-Med Ambulance number 3-6-5
traveling west on 99
about 35 minutes away.
If I go after Mary, there's no way
I'll make Jada's deadline.
I agree.
It's a lot easier to pluck her
from an ambulance
than hijacking her from a hospital.
I'll take whatever Jada throws at me.
I'm getting Mary back.
But I'm gonna need help.
Batwoman, I'm here. What do you need?
Tell Alice to stop drinking.
What the hell was that?
What do you expect when you put
the gas next to the brake?
Oh, my God. Pull over.
Relax. I know how to drive.
The damn car's an automatic.
Obviously.
I'm just reviewing my options.
You're not getting my bearings.
No. No options.
Eyes on the road.
Hands on ten and two.
Can I listen to some music, teacher?
If it means we don't have to talk.
How do you think this makes me look
to my friends? I trusted you.
I promise you,
it was nothing personal.
- The music...
- Quiet. This is juicy.
Do you even remember
what you told me that night?
She's talking about the night.
Oh, come on,
like you're not dying to know.
I said a lot of things
that night, Sophie.
Kentucky whiskey does that to a girl.
What? Don't take that, Sophie!
Then, I'll remind you.
You said you saved
a lot of people's lives
by locking Pamela away.
I could tell you meant it.
It's not too late to do it again.
Let's not act like we had
some deep connection, okay?
You couldn't be
with your first choice
and I was there.
I wonder who her first choice is.
- Oh, well.
- Don't.
My first choice?
You bitched about Ryan all night.
- Hey, that's you.
- Shut up.
And all I know is,
when I'm not into someone
I don't talk about them constantly.
She has a good point.
Whatever.
"Whatever"?
That's a big deal.
Sophie likes you back.
Back?
Who said I liked Sophie?
All the girls on the playground?
Come on, it's obvious.
You're avoiding your feelings
for Sophie
which is why you asked me
to be your wheel woman and not her.
You and I are the same, Batty.
We pretend like we don't care
but it's only because
when we get something good
we know we're gonna screw it up.
You mean, like you and Mary?
What happened between you two?
That's her.
Get closer.
Can't you just get her
with the grapple hook or something?
You want her to come flying
through the rear doors?
So particular.
Pull over!
Oh, my God, Batwoman?
I need the patient.
She needs a hospital.
Speed up.
- Seriously?
- Get in front of him.
Keep straight.
And when I land,
pull over and wait...
Oh, just make your move, bossy pants.
What the hell is going on up there?
We're being jumped by Batwoman.
Stop the car!
I... We can't.
The patient needs medical treatment.
Chester, you need to stop, right now.
Mary, it's Ryan.
Can you feel my hand?
Whoa. Poison Pam really did
a number on her.
Maybe it's for the best.
We risked our lives
trying to get her back.
Well, she's not dead.
She's just in a coma.
And if we're lucky,
she'll stay that way
so we never have to tell her
she killed a man.
What?
Oh, yeah. Mary killed a man.
A hunter. She gutted him
with a tree branch.
It's pretty horrific, actually.
Why didn't you tell me
she killed someone?
Because she doesn't know yet.
She just flung him
and didn't wait to see the damage.
Anyway, I'm guessing
if Poison Ivy Jr.
ever turns back into St. Mary
learning what she did
will pretty much destroy her.
It feels so good
to get that off of my chest.
We need water.
- What happened to her?
- No idea. She's unresponsive.
Blood in her nose, her ears.
I'm barely getting a pulse.
Mary, can you hear me?
It's called sporeling transference.
I'm sorry. What now?
Think of Mary
like a supernatural battery pack.
Being desiccated for ten years
took its toll on Pam.
The vine from Batman's trophy case
somehow found Mary
infected her, and turned her
into Pam's sporeling.
Okay, can you stop saying that word?
So Mary was created
so Pam could leech off
her life force?
No. Pam is not a parasite.
She genuinely cares about Mary.
So if Mary's life force
looks like that
can we assume
that Pam is firing on all cylinders?
On all cylinders?
She just went from a minivan
to a space rocket.
So why now?
To finish what she started.
Well, aren't you suddenly a wealth
of valuable information.
How'd you get her to talk?
Kentucky whiskey?
Pam's gonna hit the dam.
That's the only thing
outside the city on Route 99.
That's what Pam was targeting
before Batman stopped her
ten years ago.
That means she's still there.
I'm going after her.
Please tell me you're joking.
If Pam is at full strength,
you don't stand a chance.
None of you do. Not even together.
Batman tried to stop her for months
until he realized
he needed me to set the trap.
So, what do you suggest?
You wanna stop Pam, you need her.
Mary?
Mary? Can you hear us?
Why am I here?
Workers found you at the dam
and called 911.
We think Pam almost killed you.
Pam? No.
She just needed energy. I'm fine.
She's using you, Mary.
It's not like that.
I'm fine.
Seriously.
Anyway, this has been real,
but I need to find her.
She's probably wondering
where the hell I am.
She is not your friend, Mary.
She created you
because she needs you to survive.
Of course, you'd say that.
I finally find somebody who values me
so I must be in a toxic,
codependent relationship.
It can't possibly be
that this is actually who I am
and that people like me?
You're a portable battery, Mary.
And you're all out of charge.
So listen to a Kelly Clarkson song
and move on.
What are you doing here?
Who do you think told us about Pam?
You know...
guess you were right.
Guess I am the crazy one.
Says the Arkham inmate
still pretending
she's stuck
in a children's fairy tale.
A grown woman
dressed like a flying rodent.
- Okay, you made your point.
- You know what?
Don't even get me started
on Daddy's Little Robocop
or the Queen of Unemployment.
I didn't even say anything.
Yeah, but you're here, aren't you?
A part of this friend-tervention
or whatever this is.
But if you were all
actually my friends
then you'd respect my wish
when I said to leave me alone!
You killed someone, Mary.
A hunter.
An innocent man.
You didn't realize it.
You thought you just flung him
out of your way, but you didn't.
He's dead.
I think I'd know if I killed someone.
You're wrong.
You wanna stop Poison Ivy
from destroying this city?
There isn't much time left.
What the actual hell?
Hey, lady, you can't be down here.
You're gonna kill yourself.
You're here.
What happened to him?
He wanted to stop me.
I thought you were sitting this out.
I didn't see you on the bridgeway.
I realized that as much as I don't
wanna take any innocent lives
I didn't wanna put you in danger
of exerting yourself
past the point of no return.
And after everything
you've done for me
I owe you so much.
Want a boost?
Desperately.
Mary is the only one she trusts
so Mary's the only one
who can pull this off.
A few years ago, I developed
what I hoped was a pheromone-blocker.
Every morning,
I put a few drops in my coffee.
Did this for years.
Partly out of habit, partly because
I've always hoped to see Pam again.
What, I can't be sentimental?
The other day,
I found out firsthand it works.
The chemical agents blocked
Pam's ability to mind-control me.
Meaning, it must've weakened her
substantially.
So, what do we do with it?
If Mary drinks it
and Pam draws her energy
it could weaken her,
enough for you to get the upper hand.
Mary's the Trojan horse.
Pam never sees it coming.
If Pam was weakened substantially,
doesn't that mean
- that Mary will be too?
- Likely.
But between her biological reactions
to the blocker
and Pam draining whatever
Poison Ivy energy she has left
it could be the best shot
you all have
at everything being pulled out
and getting Mary back for good.
And when you say drain her energy,
how much are we talking?
If I had to guess, every last drop.
No. It could kill her.
We're not doing that.
We need to.
It's the only way to stop her.
And if she drains you to death?
I won't let her.
I'll pull away.
You can do that?
You can pull out of her grip
while she's draining you?
Pam's not stronger than me.
What's happening?
Mary, what...
what did you do?
She stopped herself
from becoming you.
I gotta go.
I'll check in when we get there.
I need to come with you.
Thought without your AI,
Batwing was on the sidelines
until you find a way
to deal with, you know...
My head. I know.
But you can't take down Poison Ivy
and also stop a dam
from imploding at once.
- Look, you don't have to do this.
- Yeah, I need to.
For me.
There is a whole mess of people
out there
willing to believe
that you deserved it
just because you're Black.
I don't wanna live in that world.
I wanna be with my dad.
Don't lie to yourself.
You wouldn't beat me
with two good hands.
There's no voice.
There's no voice...
but my voice.
Come on, Luke.
The city can't be saved, Batwoman.
It's a cesspool of crime,
filth, and pollution.
Let it go. Start fresh!
Damn!
You gotta teach me that.
Did you stop it?
Yeah. The dam's stable.
It's done.
And so is Pamela.
Mary.
Is she breathing?
- Barely.
- Let's take her home.
The city is worth saving.
At least it is to me.
I'm back.
I can feel it.
I'm me again.
Welcome back, Mary.
Never thought I'd miss
those brown eyes so much.
And we owe you a giant apology.
Mary, we will never let you
feel sidelined by this team
ever again, okay?
We're family.
Guys
I really appreciate the warm welcome
but...
I remember everything.
I know what happened.
I killed someone.
Poison Ivy killed someone.
And now, she's gone.
And Mary's back.
Yeah.
You came back to Gotham
because you care about her.
I'm sorry, who are we talking about?
Mary.
Because even though a part of you
loved every second of it
you still feel guilty
for changing her to be more like you.
Alice the Benevolent
does have a nice ring to it.
So I suppose this means
that you'll step in
and make a deal with the mayor
for my freedom.
No.
You're on your own.
Fine.
Suppose it wouldn't mean much
coming from a pumpkin anyway.
What?
Well, you missed
Mommy's 12.00 deadline
and I, for one, can't wait to see
what Jada has in store
for the Bat Team this time.
You're okay.
You're on a plane.
You did this?
Again?
My God.
How stupid am I?
Of course, you did this to me.
You sold me out.
Where are we even going?
- Can I please explain?
- No.
No more explaining.
We have explained each other
to death.
We shouldn't be together.
Well, this doesn't work.
We want two different things. You...
I'm not having this fight again.
Then, don't.
If going back and destroying
everything and everyone
is more important than me and us...
then go!
What the hell
am I supposed to do, jump?
Why? Is that crazier
than anything you've done before?
I'll 100 percent die.
Then, stay.
I didn't sell you out, Pam.
I negotiated a deal for your freedom.
No running, no rules.
But it means
doing things my way for once.
So, what's it gonna be?
Close the damn door.
Where are we going?
Sophie Moore told me
about an off-the-grid island
where plants are worshiped
and industry doesn't exist.
Sounds like a fantasy.
Close.
It's called Coryana.
I don't wanna know.
Hey, any word from Jada?
Luke is still working on the buzzer,
and she's not picking up her phone.
Okay. Well, let me know
if there's anything I can do.
Hey.
Thank you.
For whatever you said
that got Renee to talk.
Well, she's not a bad person.
She's just...
In love?
That's putting it sanely.
It didn't work.
What do you mean?
Pam's finally out of our lives.
Kissing me.
You said it would get me
out of my head, but...
it just got me in it more.
I'm sorry
if you're going through that.
No, you're not.
Hey.
We got a problem.
In a Channel 8 News exclusive.
Could that woman be responsible
for the throwback blowback?
The explosive bombshell
provided by the Jeturian CEO Jada Jet
asserts it's no coincidence
the city's been terrorized
by flashback felons from Gotham past.
Whoa, what is this?
I guess Jada's not one
to be kept waiting.
You're telling us The Mad Hatter,
Killer Croc, Mr. Freeze, Poison Ivy
they're all a result
of a major catastrophe
at the hands of Batwoman?
Batman kept his enemies' weapons
under lock and key.
Batwoman let them out of her sight
and into the hands
of would-be killers.
She's gonna turn the whole city
against me.
Just this morning, it was reported
that Batwoman stopped Poison Ivy
from rupturing the Gotham Dam.
You're missing my point.
Why was Poison Ivy at the dam
in the first place?
Didn't Batman throw her away
a decade ago?
And, yes, she stopped it
from total collapse.
But the dam still broke.
There have been reports of flooding
all over Gotham.
It's time to face this city,
Batwoman.
Admit what you've done.
Turn yourself in
before you do any more damage.