Previously on "Batwoman"...
Sophie: Alice was right.
Your mom's still alive, Ryan.
If you want to know her name.
It's not worth it.
Luke:
So, what's next, Batwoman?
Batwoman: We find
that case of Batman trophies
before anyone else does.
Why did you call me here?
Over a dozen weapons
of mass destruction
are belly-up in the
Gotham River somewhere.
So, together, you two
are gonna find
and stop every freak
who gets his hands on
one of these weapons
until each of
the items on that list
are found and accounted for.
[Laughter]
[Indistinct chatter]
Dua Lipa: ♪ if you wanna run away with me ♪
Man: Shh, shh, shh.
♪ I know a galaxy and I can
♪ take you for a ride
♪ I had a premonition that
we fell into a rhythm ♪
♪ where the music don't stop for life ♪
Nice.
Could you be a little louder?
I don't think they
heard you in Star City.
♪ Shining just the way I like
♪ if you're feeling like you
need a little bit of company ♪
♪ you met me
at the perfect time ♪
Heh.
♪ You want me
♪ I want you, baby
♪ my sugarboo, I'm levitating
How cold do you think
the pool water is?
You tell me.
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
[laughs]♪ moonlight,
you're my starlight ♪
It's actually really warm.
Good.
♪ All night
♪ Come on, dance with me
♪ I'm levitating,
you, moonlight ♪
♪ all night, come on,
dance with me ♪
♪ I'm levitating
Seriously?
Ok. I get it.
You can hold your breath
for a really long time.
But I got news for you.
The world already has
an Aquaman.
He's a lot more ripped.
Derek?
If you're waiting for me to say
this isn't funny, then fine.
This isn't funny.
You can come up now.
Ohh! Aah! Aah!
Aah!
[Both screaming]
[Door opens]
Renee: By the order of
the mayor's office,
in exchange for your cooperation
in these cases,
you will be remanded
into supervised custody.
Woman: This is a wild one.
Renee: If you harm
or attempt to harm any person,
this release will be rescinded.
If you violate any of the laws
of Gotham City,
this release will be rescinded.
[Shackles clattering]
If you attempt to escape,
this release will be rescinded
and you will spend
the remainder of your life
at arkham in
solitary confinement.
Any questions?
Yes.
Does this kind of wreck
my ensemble?
Any questions I'm
likely to answer?
Ryan: I got one.
What makes you think
any of this is gonna stick?
You.
Because you're responsible
for everything she does.
She crosses the line, your days
as a caped vigilante are over.
I might even arrange for you two
to have adjoining cells.
You're tying my fate
to a psychopath?
Well, more like
handcuffing it, but yes.
Until you two have tracked down
every last one
of those toxic toys
from Batman's trophy case.
'Cause it looks like
another one's already
racking up a body count.
Dana DeWitt:
In a crime as cold-blooded
as the creature some say
is responsible,
two Gotham university students
are missing
and presumed dead
after blood and not much else
was found at the scene,
save for a grisly calling card
which eerily resembles that
of Batman foe killer Croc,
who terrorized Gotham
nearly two decades ago
in a violent reign
of reptilian terror.
And while some insist
this may just be the work
of an attention-seeking copycat,
authorities can't say for sure
whether Gotham has
a new lizard problem
or if this killer
is just a Crock.
And while initial searches for...
Luke:
Killer Kroc, a.k.a. Waylon Jones.
Former professional wrestler
who suffered from
an unidentified infection
that caused his skin
to grow scales,
hence the appearance
of a crocodile.
Now, as
the infection progressed,
other physical
abnormalities followed...
Elongated jaw, claws, tail.
I remember him.
Batman killed him, right?
Oh, no.
No. No, Bruce
tried to save him.
He took pity on him.
He always thought
that his violent tendencies
were a result of the infection.
He actually had waynetech labs
working on a cure
for his condition.
A way to reverse it. But...
They never found it, though.
So, what happened?
The G.C.P.D. happened.
They had their own ideas
of how to deal with K.C.,
so, they dropped
a truckload of thermite
into the sewer junction.
Right on top of him.
Lit the primer cord and ran.
So, that tooth?
Pretty much all that
was left of him.
And now it's loose.
Ok, but how could a tooth
have created a whole
'nother Croc?
I mean, I get a lizard
can grow back a whole new tail,
but please tell me that tooth
didn't grow back
a whole new killer Croc.
If the original killer Croc
suffered from an infection,
then it would've gotten
into his bloodstream.
So, maybe the tooth
carried the infection.
And whoever found it...
We need to find them.
But the question is, how?
Alice: I have a question.
Why is there a tree in here?
I mean, I get
the whole bat motif,
but this is a, um,
44-story building.
Surely there's a more
comfortable workspace available.
I need to talk to you both.
In private.
I'm just gonna hang out here.
[Sigh]
Ok. If new Croc's anything
like the old one,
I'm gonna need batwing on my 6.
Where are you with figuring out
what's wrong with the suit?
Uh, still working on it
but making progress.
Ok, well, why don't you two
put your nerd brains together
and try to fast-track a fix.
Yeah.
Yeah, we'll get on it.
Sophie: Knock-knock.
Got my hands on a copy of
the forensics report
from the pool attack.
Fair warning...
The word "secretion"
comes up in several places,
because apparently, his drool
contains a paralytic agent
which renders his
victims unconscious,
allowing him to
feed on them at his leisure.
Mary: I should probably
put it out there right now
that I really do not
do reptiles.
Ok. Let's get Alice on this.
If crazy stuff's going down,
may as well get the crazy
lady's take on it.
Um, we don't really use
the "C" word anymore.
"Crazy"?
[Helicopter blades whirring]
What the hell?
Luke: Seems we have a guest.
Security cleared
a landing request
for the CEO of
Jeturian Industries.
Jada jet.
She's apparently
insisting on a meeting
with the Wayne ceo
and will not leave
until she has one.
Ryan:
Good luck with that.
Mary: Well, we can't exactly
tell her, "we don't know
where our billionaire
ceo is."
I have a feeling she'll settle
for the acting ceo.
Ryan: Great.
Sophie: Who's the acting ceo?
Me.
Kate wanted to make sure
we could handle
any problems that
arose in her absence.
Thought I'd just be
the name on the letterhead.
Ok. Well,
if Jada jet
wants to meet Wayne's top-op,
I'm gonna need to look the part.
Oh! Actually,
you are in luck,
because I just picked up
a ton of dry cleaning.
And why don't you
try to find out
what our uninvited guest wants.
Ok.
Hey. I know you said
you didn't want to know this,
but before you
sit down with her,
you should probably know that...
That uninvited guest
is your birth mother.
Ok. Tell the truth.
Does this say, "no,
I haven't been ceo
for just 5 minutes"?
No. It says,
"I'm a confident,
"put-together, young black woman
who you were an idiot
to ever give up."
You think she knows?
Pretty big coincidence
if she doesn't.
What does she want?
What do you want?
I just want to get
through this meeting
and never see her again.
And I want to get
her damn helicopter
off of my roof.
Ok. Um, ahem,
what is the absolute minimum
I need to know
to get through this unscathed?
What would Bruce Wayne
insist on knowing about her?
Probably her bra size.
Wiki version:
Jeturian Industries
specializes in microtechnology.
Jada jet took control
after the death of her husband
a decade ago.
Doubled the company's wealth
in half that time.
She's a fighter.
But so are you.
Send her in.
Hey. Just remember,
she never gave you anything,
so, she can't take
anything away.
You got this.
Nessa Barrett:
♪ talk how you talk
♪ walk how you walk
♪ 'cause I'd have
a problem sleeping ♪
♪ if we're counting crimes,
nickels and dimes ♪
♪ we both have riches,
but you'd be the... ♪
Jada: If I had known
Wayne had a new ceo,
I would have sent a gift basket.
♪ I could never love
then we couldn't meet in person.
Ryan. And it's acting ceo.
So, Bruce Wayne
checks his stock price
from a superyacht in Belize
while you do all the real work?
Jada jet.
Nice to meet you.
Were you and Bruce acquainted?
We exchanged a few heated words
years ago when he poached
one of my most valued employees.
If your employee allowed himself
to be poached,
he must've felt undervalued.
But I'm assuming you
didn't fly 12 blocks
from your corporate headquarters
to open up old wounds.
No. I'm here
to address a new one.
There was an illegal breach
of the Jeturian Industries servers.
It was a very
sophisticated hack.
But the culprit
left behind a few
digital bread crumbs,
and we followed them back
to an ip address
belonging to Wayne enterprises.
That's why you're here?
Well, it depends.
Is there anything else
I should know about?
Because I think
corporate espionage
is more than enough reason
to have a little chat.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Mm. Ignorance of
what's going on in your company
doesn't pass for
business acumen.
If you had proof,
you'd be talking
to the sec, not me.
Why are you here?
Because I didn't
forge my company
into a multinational conglomerate
to have someone swoop in
and steal my life's work.
And because...
I believe warnings are
best delivered directly.
And I'll only give one.
Stay out of my business.
That won't be a problem.
And I think you should
drop the "acting"
from your job title.
Denying you knew
anything about this...
Was not your best performance.
[Elevator bell dings]
Your dad programmed
your suit's ai
to speak with his voice?
Uh, dad, say hello to Mary.
[Whirring] Hello, Mary.
Give it a try.
Mr. Fox?
Hi.
What was Luke like as a kid?
[Whirring]
Calling up photo records
for Lucas fox, age 6.
Dad, belay that request, please.
It's like you can
talk to him again.
It's... it's amazing.
It would be more amazing
if the suit didn't
turn off at the worst
possible times.
Any guesses why?
According to this diagnostic,
the suit's failsafe got tripped,
causing it to shut down.
Mary: What tripped it?
Luke: Well, the suit tracks
all kinds of medical data...
Biometrics, eye movement,
electromagnetic impulses
to the brain, heart rate.
It's just constantly monitoring
the health status of
the person wearing it.
If I'm reading this right,
the suit thought
you were injured.
Yeah, which prompted
a system-wide shutdown,
putting the suit in safe mode.
Turning off in
the middle of a fight
because it thinks you
need medical assistance
seems more like unsafe mode.
Yeah.
Well, there's a reason
that this thing
was under a tarp in my dad's lab
and not out on patrol in Gotham.
Still have some glitches
to work out.
Well, why don't we
start by making sure
there aren't any glitches
with you first.
If the suit thinks
you're injured,
let's make sure you're not.
Uhh. Uhh. Ahh. [Exhales]
[Alice exhales] Ryan:
So, let's get this monster.
Oh. I thought she found you.
Did I spy with my little eye
Jada jet's chopper on the roof?
So, you knew her name
this entire time?
She's kind of like
a helicopter parent,
just without the parent.
I mean, really.
What kind of mother
abandons their daughter
to the horrors
of the foster care system
to literally
jet-set around the globe?
No. No.
We're not doing this.
Renee said I have to watch you.
It doesn't mean
I have to listen to you.
So, you don't want to know
where Croc's gonna strike next?
Fine.
Well, as the resident expert
on predatory behavior,
I had some thoughts
on how Mr., uh, [rawr]
Chooses his prey.
I was thinking back
to my first kill,
for which I chose
a geriatric harpy
with an oxygen tank. Now,
do you know why I did that?
Because you're a killer, Alice.
No. Well, yes, but
that's not the takeaway.
I chose her because she was
easy pickings.
See, when a fledgling predator
is learning how
to stalk its prey,
it seeks to, um,
separate one from the herd.
So, he wouldn't have gone after
two victims for his first hunt.
Look at you learning
to think like a killer.
Which means the pool
wasn't this Croc's first attack.
And if it wasn't for
all the blood
in the deep end...
They would've just
been listed as
missing persons.
Just like
the missing persons I found
that were last seen
at the east river shore.
A mere two miles
from the pool attack.
Welcome to his hunting ground.
Girl: And with the team
trailing by one,
an incredible cross-field pass
from Megan rapinoe
to rookie sensation
Whitney hutchinson,
who fakes out the last defender,
and she's on breakaway...
And scores!
The crowd goes wild.
We're all tied up with
minutes left in the game.
Woman: Which the refs
are calling
on account of darkness.
Whitney: Mom!
Woman: Mm-mm.
Arguing with the ref
will get you
a yellow card.
Fine.
Gross.
Aah!
Sophie: According
to the 911 call,
you're right in the area where
the missing girl's mother
said she was playing.
Gcpd's en route.
Well, they'll find
about as much as we have,
which isn't much.
There has to be some sign
of her there.
Batwoman: Drag marks lead off
in that direction.
But there's no
body parts, no blood.
He didn't feed on her here.
Which is understandable,
given he did just
feast on all-you-can-eat coeds.
There's a whole lot of
secretion, Sophie.
Didn't you say O.G.
Killer Croc's Saliva
contained a paralytic agent?
That's how he
subdued his victims.
And then stash them
away for later.
It's basically like
a Croc-pantry,
for when he wants a doggy-bag.
Ok, then we need to find
where he stashed her,
because that girl
could still be alive.
Yeah.
Until he gets hungry.
Is that Croc skin?
It appears our Croc is a...
Growing boy.
Whitney: Aah!
[Splash]
[Gasping for air]
Aah! Oh! [Crying]
[Growling]
Alice: So, what was
she like? Mommy.
She was amazing.
And then you took her from me.
I meant birth mommy.
But if it'll break the ice,
I'll tell you about my mom.
She had a really great
head on her shoulders.
Emphasis on
the word "had."
Why do you care?
Why do you keep
pretending not to?
Surely you grew up wondering
what she was like, and
seeing as fate,
otherwise known as me,
has brought you together,
I think I at least
deserve to know that
my efforts have paid off.
You want to know
what Jada was like?
She was amazing.
She was confident, direct,
fearless, unapologetic.
She was a freaking masterclass
in taking what's hers.
And letting it go, apparently.
Did it hurt all the more knowing
she didn't want you in her life?
No. Because I don't
want her in mine.
She doesn't even know who I am,
but I know who she is
and I don't need her.
Now shut up and help
me find the trail.
Actually... i think we just
found where it ends.
[Grate clattering]
You first.
Me? The one who's
not wearing impenetrable
tactical armor?
That's who you want
taking point?
I'm not letting you
out of my sight, Alice.
Do you really think
I'm gonna run?
I'm going to believe
that you give a damn
about stopping this Croc?
Yes. I think
you're gonna run
the first chance you get.
So, it's my job not to
give you any chances.
Oh, that's funny.
I thought it was your job
to save a little girl.
Don't act like you're here
to do the good deed, Alice.
You only think about yourself,
so, don't you dare use
that little girl as camouflage.
I was that little girl.
Don't act like
you're the only one
with abandonment issues.
I will not give up on this girl
the way everyone gave up on me.
Ucch! That smell.
Rotting meat.
Kinda takes me back
to my childhood.
What the hell is this?
Bait.
This means we're
not the only one
hunting this monster.
Man: He's not a monster.
He's my son.
This feels a bit unnecessary.
I'm fine.
Well, you're keeping fit.
In... my official,
professional
medical opinion.
Let's take a look
at your heart rate.
[Monitor beeping]
It looks good.
Let's have a listen
to your lungs.
Good breath sounds.
Mm. Your heart rate
is rising.
[Monitor beeping faster]
Rising...[monitor beeping faster]
Still rising.[Monitor beeping faster]
Now it's racing.
Luke, are you ok?
I... i... yeah, yeah.
I... I'm just... I'm ticklish
and your hands are cold.
Yeah. Yeah.
You're right. I...
You're totally fine.
Totally... you're totally
feeling fine.
You can put your shirt back on.
Yeah. Ok.
If you want.
You should.
Uh... yeah.
So, like I said,
it's just a problem
with the suit.
Ahh. Yeah.
Must be.
You think you can fix it?
Yeah. Yeah.
It should be easy.
I just need to
override the failsafe.
Are you sure that
that's a good idea?
I mean, isn't the point
of a failsafe
to keep you safe
when the suit fails?
What if it's just
trying to protect you?
I think it's being
a little overprotective.
Kind of reminds me of a certain
newly minted doctor that I know.
[Sigh]
My boy didn't mean
to hurt those people.
I'm sure he didn't.
He's not a killer.
Unlike that one.
I wasn't expecting to
find anybody down here,
much less a pair of celebrities.
What the hell are you two
doing together, anyway?
Aren't y'all supposed
to be enemies?
Long story.
She's working with me.
They're a little short-staffed
at City Hall.
That's why.
We want to help your son.
Why don't you start
by telling us
what happened to him?
It's probably better I show you.
[Sigh] Just before Steven
was heading off to college,
we went on a father-son
fishing trip.
He hooked a bluegill
on his very first cast.
But when we cut that thing open,
there was something
mighty weird inside.
Batwoman: Let me guess.
A rather large crocodile tooth?
Yeah. Steven thought
it would be cool
to make it into a necklace.
But he cut himself on the tooth.
Cut got infected.
Then Steven... Started changing.
[Sigh] Tried doctors.
None of them knew what it was.
They couldn't stop the changes.
Every day, there was
a little less Steven
and a little more... Creature.
And that's when the
appetite took hold of him.
And I had to chain him up.
But he was just too strong.
Too hungry.
He broke free.
I've been trying
to lure him back.
Alice: You really rolled out
the red carpet for him.
I can't imagine what
you're going through.
But we really do want
to help your son,
and we have to start
by making sure
he doesn't hurt that little girl
or anyone else.
Alice: Yeah, but I just
don't think he's gonna
agree to being locked up again.
That's where this comes in.
[Electricity crackling]
You think that thing's
strong enough for him?
Yeah. But it's not for him.
It's for you.
Aah!
I'm not gonna let you
hurt my boy.
[Electricity crackling]
Aah! Oh!
Batwoman, I'm reading
a huge power spike.
Is everything ok?
Batwoman, do you read me?
Batwoman!
[Groaning]
Man: I'm sorry.
I really am.
But my boy's suffered enough
without you adding to it.
[Groaning]
I just want to get him
the help he needs.
Man: Yeah. Your idea
of helping Stevie
is taking him away from me.
Locking him in a cage, or worse.
Jab him with needles.
Dissect him like he's
some kind of lab animal.
[Electricity crackling]
[Screaming]
[Gasping]
Man: I'm his father
and I'm gonna do
whatever I need to do
to keep him safe.
Even if that means...
[growling]
Stevie, it's your dad.
Stevie, noooo!
No! [Screaming]
[Croc growling]
That is your son, yeah.
[Groaning]
Are you ok?
Yeah. I just
need a minute.
Oh, that's good.
'Cause that's all I need.
[Electricity crackling]
Suckas.
One minute I had her and then
everything went dead.
I've been trying to raise her
but I can't even...
[static]
Batwoman: Batcave. Come in.
Batwoman, we read you.
What happened?
Exactly what I said
would happen.
Alice escaped.
And I can't hunt her down
and save a little girl.
Batwing, you ready to
get back to the field?
Yeah. I'm good to go.
So, you and Mary fixed
what was wrong with the suit.
Um... yes.
Batwing is all clear.
Batwoman: Good.
Alice was last headed
north through the sewer tunnels.
Sophie: If she's on foot,
she's gonna wanna change that.
There's a truck depot a few
miles on that trajectory.
That's where I'd head.
I hope you're right.
We need to find Alice
before Renee knows she's gone.
Whitney: Help! Somebody!
Please, please.
Oh, thank god.
I thought that thing
was gonna come back.
And he probably will do so, hon.
Up and at 'em.
We gotta skedaddle.
I can't walk.
You're gonna have to try.
But my leg is broken.
[Croc growling]
[Whitney whimpering]
Alice: ...Hey, hon.
I'm on a really tight
schedule here, so,
you and I three-legged
racing outta here
is really gonna slow me down.
No, no.
You have to help me.
[Panting]
Fine. I'm gonna help you.
By teaching you the lesson that
I had to learn the hard way.
No one is gonna
save you except yourself.
You are the only one
you can count on.
The sooner you learn that,
the better off you'll be.
No.
You're gonna thank me
for this one day.
[Crying] No! No!
Help me, please!
Don't leave me...
Don't leave me, please!
[Croc growling]
Batwoman: I know
you're out there, Steven,
and I know you can hear me.
There is still some of you
left in there that
can understand me.
Ok? I do not want to hurt you.
I just want to help you.
And your father, he just
wants to help you, too.
He really loves you.
And trust me... you are
really lucky
to have a parent like that.
Someone that would do
anything to protect you.
And never give up on you.
No matter what.
[Sigh] So much for
trying to reason with you.
Woman: Montoya.
We got a problem.
Just lost the signal from
Alice's tracking monitor.
Define "lost."
One moment it's reading
loud and clear.
The next, nothing.
It doesn't make sense.
No one's ever managed
to circumvent
one of those things.
Tell that to Alice.
This means she could
be anywhere.
[Grate scraping, clattering]
Oh, great.
The sidekick.
It's batwing.
Ooh. Cool name.
Now let's see if
you can live up to it.
[Both grunting]
[Clank]
Uhh!
How's the suit, Luke?
Any problems?
Just this distracting
voice in my ear.
[Both grunting]
[Electricity crackling]
Did you really think
you could beat me?
Why would I need to beat you?
We're on the same team,
whether we like it or not.
Was something supposed
to happen?
It already has.
Right now,
1,000 nanobots are
swimming through
your bloodstream,
sending out tracking beacons
to satellites as we speak.
So, if you wanna run,
you better be really fast.
[Grunting]
[Croc growling]
[Whitney screaming]
[Batwoman grunting]
[Croc growling]
Uhh!
Uhh! Uhh!
[Growling]
[Grunting]
Uhh!
[Growling]
You ok?
[Gasping for air]
It's ok.
I got you.
Woman: I thought I lost you.
[Whitney crying softly]
[Sirens wailing]
Congratulations.
I see you've stopped the Croc,
secured the tooth,
reunited a missing girl
with her mother,
but... what I don't see
is your partner.
She's over there.
Waiting for you to chauffeur her
back to arkham.
Had some technical
difficulties with that,
but I think we've found
a better solution.
Right, Alice?
Vesper Fairchild:
Leapin' lizards, Gotham!
You can add "bat" to
the list of apex predators,
because Batwoman
just took a bite
out of Croc 2.0.
The rampaging reptile
has been relocated
to the not-so-natural habitat
of arkham asylum,
where I'm assuming the guards'
hazard pay just went up.
Thanks to the caped crusader,
the Croc was denied
his last meal
and missing girl
Whitney hutchinson
was reunited with her mother
in a reunion that had
even the likes of yours truly
a little weepy.
Rest assured, Gotham,
these were not crocodile tears.
You know...
If you squint,
you can just make out
Jeturian Industries from here.
I liked it better
when I didn't know
she was there.
I'm sorry.
I should've never told you.
It's not your fault.
It's nobody fault.
Except hers.
Woman: ♪ slow motion dreaming
you know what I can't get over?
She paid a doctor $2 million
to falsify her records so no one
would ever know I was hers.
What kind of mom does that?
♪ I know, I know that...
You don't know what
her life was like then,
or what she was going through,
or even what her options were.
But there is one person who can
give you those answers.
♪ Don't give up now
I don't know if
I want to know them.
Ryan, I know what it's like
to need to put up a wall.
Believe me, I've laid a few
bricks in my life.
But I also know what it's like
to be a girl who just
wants a hug from her mom.
♪ Needed a lie
♪ more than my thoughts
what if she doesn't
want me as her daughter?
♪ Holding on
then it'll be her loss.
Not yours.
♪ Needed a lie
♪ more than my thoughts
Luke: Sorry I banged up
the suit a little bit.
♪ Needed a lie
dad.♪ more than my thoughts
dad?
Mary: Ohh. Why isn't he talking?
I don't know.
Maybe it's because you removed
the failsafe.
And I think you need
to turn it back on.
I managed to pinpoint
where the suit
still thinks you're injured
and it's the exact
same place where you were shot.
Yeah, but that injury's healed.
I know.
But thanks to the desert Rose,
you don't even have a scar.
Right.
A physical one, anyway.
I think what the suit
is interpreting
as physical pain is actually
psychological pain.
Mary, come on.
That's absurd.
Is it?
You've been through so much.
Just because your body is healed
doesn't mean you have.
Woman: This is a problem.
Botanist in the lab
doesn't think
this vine is one of
poison Ivy's.
Only way to be 100% sure is
to run tests on it,
but the only way to do that...
Is to open it.
But he wasn't
willing to do that.
How'd you know it
wasn't the real thing?
Because I've seen it up close.
And if the real thing
is still out there...
God help us.
[Door opens]
Man: Wait. Excuse me. Miss.
I'm afraid you can't
just go in there.
I'm sorry, Ms. Jet.
She just walked right in.
It's all right.
I dropped in
on Ms. Wilder
unannounced yesterday.
She's just returning the favor.
I thought you and I agreed
you'd stay out of my business.
I am.
This is personal.
Because I'm your daughter.
Man: Greg, move your head.