- Help!
- Help me!
Pam!
What are you doing?
I thought the water would revive me.
I was wrong.
I need to get my strength back.
How did you do it, Mama?
Three jobs, volunteering at church,
raising me.
You were literally everything
to everyone
and you didn't break a sweat.
I just...
I can't get out of my damn head.
What am I doing wrong?
Pretty sure in the real world,
this would be an HR violation
of appropriate workplace behavior.
Good thing it's not the real world.
Well, hurry up.
You're breathing like Darth Vader
and making me feel bad
about that bagel I had for breakfast.
Great. Then you can help.
- You wanna talk about it?
- Nope.
- Does Ryan know?
Does this have something to do
with Marquis Jet?
Never thought I would see
the Jada Jet look so defeated.
When I got your message
you sound like
you've been put
through a wringer or two.
John Diggle.
It's good to see you, old friend.
So...
Why don't you tell me...
how an old friend can help?
Sunlight's not working.
It's been 10 years, Pam.
Give yourself some time.
Time? I've got nothing but time.
Something's wrong.
My energy's depleting so quickly.
Didn't stop you from attacking
two innocent fishermen.
The lake's catch and release.
They were creating an imbalance
in an already vulnerable species.
Ten years and suddenly
it's like yesterday.
What were you thinking would happen
when you freed me?
I wasn't.
I wrapped up in the moment
seeing you
the white tulip, the memories,
the guilt...
Oh. I'm so sorry that you had
to feel guilt, Renee
while I rotted for a decade
with no water, sunlight
or soulmate.
That must have been
really awful for you.
I am sorry, Pam.
How am I supposed to believe that?
I needed you, more than anything.
And you're the one
that put me there.
I know how to get your strength back.
I come bearing sustenance.
Very mature.
I was able to keep Jada off our backs
while we hunt Pam Isley.
Dead fisherman on Loeb Lake.
Found with weeds tangled
around his legs.
So this is happening?
You're gonna give me
the silent treatment
for the rest of our lives?
A little busy, Soph.
Your girlfriend Renee is on the loose
with an eco-terrorist.
She's not my girlfriend.
So can we assume that the dead
fisherman is the OG Ivy and not Mary
considering he's, you know, dead?
There was also an
unnatural hornet attack
reported at a pesticide factory
last night.
Injured six employees.
Matches what I found.
A nearby drilling operation
got shut down
because of a tipped oil rig.
Okay. All these attacks
are environment-based.
- That's Pam Isley's MO.
- I'll triangulate these sites.
Even if we do find her, then what?
I'm actually working on that.
The darts are filled with
a paralytic drug and a herbicide.
So it won't kill her
and it will slow down her system
long enough for us to figure out
how to recreate
the desiccation serum.
Good news, bad news.
All of these attacks are within
a two-mile radius
of a general location.
Supposed to start with the bad news.
Bad news is, this is the location.
The national park?
We're going to be hunting
Mother Nature
in the middle of Mother Nature?
I'm down if you are.
Ever watch a horror movie?
When black people go into the woods,
they usually don't come out.
black people never write
those movies.
What do you say we flip the script?
I had no idea things
have gotten this bad.
When Marquis wakes up
there's no doubt
he'll go after his sister.
That's why I called you.
I want to offer you a job
as head of my security detail.
You'd be protecting Ryan, me,
the company
like old times, except Franklin's
not in charge, I am.
Well then it's exactly
like old times.
I know there's a way to fix my boy.
Call it hubris or naivete,
or mother's will
but I will not lock him up
in an Arkham cell
for something that wasn't his fault.
Jada...
I appreciate you thinking of me.
Thank you.
But I can't accept.
When you offered to come by
in person, I got my hopes up.
Well, I just so happen
to be in Gotham
for other matters.
Have you ever thought about
helping your son's psychosis
by going back to the source?
The Joker's joy buzzer?
That's what I'm trying to do.
Every neurologist I've talked to says
that another jolt would reawaken
his empathy.
But I have spent millions
looking for the buzzer
but no one's seen it since the Joker
disappeared years ago.
- It's gone.
- Maybe it's not.
I've been following your news.
The Mad Hatter, Killer Croc,
Mr. Freeze, all Batman's enemies.
And now their weapons just show up
out of nowhere?
Do you think they're part
of some collection?
I think they were. Yeah.
And somehow they made their way
out to the street.
And considering The Joker
was Batman's greatest enemy
maybe the buzzer
is out there now too.
I had some folks over at ARGUS
look into this.
A former police officer,
Renee Montoya
now works for the mayor's
off-books "Rogues Unit"
looking at all of these events.
Maybe it's worth the two of us
popping by to say hello.
I read about this phenomenon
where plants communicate
through acoustics in the ground.
Wind blows at a certain frequency,
fungi send distress signals.
It's called "Natural Networking".
It's kind of hot.
You...
reading glasses on, head in a book...
thinking about fungi...
I figured the cutting Batman
saved infected Mary Hamilton
for a reason.
My sporeling.
Your what?
A piece of me created her to bring me
back to health.
Like a battery
without a plug.
If I can draw her here,
she'll revive me.
Let's hope this works then.
No, no, no, no.
One triple-shot frappe.
Extra sweet cream. And conveniently,
free of charge.
Oh, and I have a gift for you.
How about an all-inclusive vacation
to Santorini?
Why Santorini?
Cute bikinis, non-stop sunshine,
far, far away from Gotham...
Need I go on?
Nope.
But I'm in charge of the music.
I refuse to listen to a boy band
sing about condiments for two hours.
Brain freeze.
Not a brain freeze.
What the hell is going on?
I have no idea.
Look, I admit I royally screwed up
with Renee.
Sleeping with her...
trusting her, defending her,
everything.
Seriously, my bad. All right?
Yep.
That's it? Yep?
I'm trying to be real with you.
I appreciate that.
But it doesn't take away
from the fact
that we are driving into the woods
to fight Poison Ivy
who Renee freed and probably told
everything to.
My identity, our plan,
our vulnerabilities...
Look out!
You have to help me, please.
Oh, my God.
You're okay. We got you.
We need to get out of here.
We're not safe.
What do you mean?
Who did this to you?
Sophie!
Run!
- I can't.
- No. We have to keep moving.
Come on. Come on.
Luke, gun!
Gun! Go!
Luke, we gotta go.
We gotta go. Luke, we gotta go.
Guys, be careful. Let's go!
Now what?
Luke.
You wanna tell us what's going on?
Well, just saw an innocent man
get impaled with a root.
So, three guesses.
That wasn't your fault.
This is all my fault.
How did you not get that?
Okay. What is the common denominator
of all our problems?
The Batwing suit breaks half the time
because of me.
We couldn't save Mary from Poison Ivy
A fricking vine snagged
the dart gun away because of me.
My dad knew it all along.
There is one reason
he didn't give me the suit
and one reason only...
I am not a hero.
You know how you know you're
on the journey to being a hero?
You fail.
Look at Sophie.
Alice and Pam
both escaped on her watch
and she worked security
for five years.
True.
And Ryan,
the supposed team detective
didn't even notice that
her own roommate
was infected with Poison Ivy
until it was way too late.
Talk about screwing up big time.
See? No one's perfect.
You can't spiral on us.
We need your obnoxiously superior
brain to get us out of here.
All right, well, shotgun, handful of
shells, vinegar, baking powder, saw
and a whole bunch of other crap
from this cabin.
You think you can figure out
another way to take her down?
I can try.
I take it you didn't find Mary.
I had other company.
What did you do?
How did Batwoman know where I'd be?
Pam...
answer me right now.
What did you do?
They're fine.
But now you've got me wondering
why you're so concerned.
They're not bad people.
Batman buried me alive.
I told you, Ryan is not Batman.
And what do you think
she's gonna do to me?
- Let me talk to her...
- And tell her what?
That you can change.
I am sorry, Pam, for hurting you.
I will regret what I did
for the rest of my life.
But you can't keep going down
this path.
I want you to be healthy and safe.
I want us to be able to heal
and leave this city behind.
Can't I, alone, be worth it?
Of course you're worth it.
And one day,
we will leave this city behind.
But right now, I need to make sure
no one standing in my way.
Stay put.
Don't move a muscle.
I'm going to kill Batwoman,
and then we can work on us.
Looks like the city doesn't
have much hope for the Rogues Unit.
She's not here.
You got a hairpin
in that fancy thing?
Thank you.
Give me.
You can take the girl out
of the streets
but you can't take
the street out of the girl.
You haven't changed one bit,
haven't you?
I got back with my wife.
Lucky her.
Looks like we're in the right place.
Like you said...
these belonged to Batman
then somehow managed
to fall into the river
and into the hands
of would-be killers.
I think a certain hero
has some explaining to do.
Okay.
I feel better since we turned.
Hey. Good. Yeah.
Santorini here we come.
Okay, it's back. Turn back.
Do you want to run out of gas?
Alice, I'm serious.
- Stop the car.
- No.
I said stop!
Stop!
I am supposed to be the crazy one.
You're not the one
with the bitch of a migraine
that only seems to stop bitching
when I go this way.
If you go that way,
you'll probably die.
The OG is back.
She's trying to draw you to her.
Why?
Do I look like the president
of the Poison Ivy fan club?
I don't know.
But I do know that a world
with two of a kind never ends well.
Why don't you ask poor boring
Beth Kane.
Oh, that's right,
you can't because she's dead.
And that's why
I've been feeling this way?
Clearly, we have some sort of bond
and she's calling out to me.
Give me the keys.
Were you not listening
to anything I said?
I am going, Alice.
This is the woman
who unlocked my prowess.
And the reason
why I'm finally happy.
The least I can do is go
and see what she wants, right?
Fine.
Let's go meet your maker.
Tequila?
Is this the part where I say yes
and you pass it to Luke?
It's where I thank you
for grabbing my bat suit
while your car
was being sucked into the abyss.
You're a bad ass.
Can I ask you something?
What's your problem with me?
Hey, I haven't brought up Renee once
since we got here.
I'm not talking about Renee.
And you can pretend all you want
that our problems started
when she came into our lives
but it's been like this
since the beginning.
Hey. You mean back when you
thought I was a common criminal.
Is that why you don't like me?
I have apologized.
I've changed.
Ryan, I literally quit my job
in part because of this relationship
and what I've learned from you.
I'm trying, okay?
But I'm not getting anything
in return.
What do you want in return?
What do you want?
Look, no offense
but, Sophie, I have so much going on
in my head right now.
I don't know what I want.
You think?
Half the time I don't know
if you like me or hate me.
And honestly,
I think you're just afraid.
Afraid of what?
Of feeling something real
and blowing it.
So what is it? What do you want?
Move.
- What?
- Move.
Salt and vinegar.
Why are we whispering?
Imagine of each of the trillion
spores in these woods
as one of Poison Ivy's
sensory glands.
She can sense sound vibrations.
Yeah. So between the hammering
and the arguing.
We drew her right to us.
Well, game on, bitch.
Load up two more of those,
we're going on a Poison Ivy hunt.
I wish I could, but unfortunately,
that was the last of the salt.
Wait, actually, that's not true.
I saw a bag of ice melt
in the truck in the driveway.
The truck in the driveway outside.
Out there.
On the other side of these walls.
Or we can just stay cooped up in here
and second-guess each other to death.
Save Pam the effort.
Okay. We could draw straws
to see who goes?
I'll save us the trouble.
I'm Batwoman. I'll go.
She's close.
I can feel her warm pull.
What are you doing?
Well, she named herself Poison Ivy.
Why not Delicate Lilac
or Dainty Lilly?
Maybe because she's a mass murderer.
Alice, you're not tire-ironing the
woman responsible for my awakening.
Look, I get this whole bone
of my bone, flesh of my flesh thing
that's happening right now.
But this is an ending
with the two of you
winding your little vines together
making a peace wreath.
Are you jealous?
What is happening here?
What are you so worried about?
You ending up dead.
Because the tickets to Santorini
are in your name
and if you die,
I will miss out on a spa retreat, so.
Why do we work, Alice?
You killed my mom.
I replaced you in our family.
But...
here we are on this crazy adventure
together, why?
Probably because you made me drive
out to your deliverance country.
It's because despite
all of our baggage...
we both found the sister
we always wanted.
I see the girl
who just craves her freedom.
And I love that you support me
to do what I want.
And this is what I want.
I hate to have to pull this card,
sis, but tough beans.
- I'm older.
- Alice, stop.
What are you doing?
You're staying right here.
I'm going alone.
And you're not gonna stop me.
Nighty night.
Finally making yourself useful.
Well, they had no Bordeaux
in that mini fridge over there.
Let's see if she has an opener
around here.
So how'd she find you?
Your daughter.
Daughter?
I've never actually heard her
described to me that way.
Well, do you mind me asking
what's keeping you
from treating her that way?
Look at me, John.
I just broke into City Hall
to find a way to keep my son
from becoming another monster
on the cork board.
The closer I get to Ryan, the faster
she becomes a potential victim.
And yet you smiled just now
when I brought up her name.
I actually don't know
how she found me.
But...
maybe there is a part of me
that's happy that she did.
Well, maybe.
Hear me out of here.
Just maybe.
If you drop your guard for a minute
and open yourself up
to other possibilities.
That thing you thought
would be your worst nightmare
might just be the best thing
to ever happen to you, Jada.
Forget that beer, John.
We're gonna need that Bordeaux
after all.
We're celebrating.
Hey, where's Pam?
I can't let you find her.
Good luck.
Here I am, trying to teach
you an important life skill.
And you're more interested
in my phone.
Mommy said we have to make memories.
Memories, bud.
But your mother is right.
As always.
Hey.
Stay where you are.
Hello?
What the hell happened to you, girl?
Get away from me.
Dad!
What is she doing?
Her damn arms aren't long enough.
I can hear you.
I can't watch.
If you could grab both,
that would be even better.
You grab both.
Okay, one it is.
What in the actual hell?
Batwoman, help!
Oh, my God.
Run!
Luke, get ready to run.
- Sophie, I need you.
- Talk to me.
- Blow up the truck.
- What?
You asked me what I wanted?
Blow up the truck!
The suit will protect me.
- We don't know that.
- Blow up the damn truck!
How the hell am I suppose...
Shoot it, hot shot.
You good?
You saved me.
Here you go.
Hey.
The park rangers
are looking for your dad.
And they're gonna find him, okay?
Sophie, checking in. Any sign of her?
Ryan.
Luke, I found her. She's alive.
I'm okay. I'm fine.
Fine?
That's all you have to say?
You almost died.
She's too strong for us.
We need to make it home.
Make a replica of Luke's gun
and find some more of that serum.
Ryan, look at me.
Never put me in that position again.
It stopped her, didn't it?
- You could have died.
- But I didn't.
- But you could have.
- Oh, well.
What? Ryan, no.
You don't get to,
oh, well me and walk away.
What is going on with you?
I'm freaking exhausted, Sophie.
You wanna know what I want?
I want to sleep.
That's what I want.
I have a family, I didn't ask
for trying to destroy my city.
My best friend is off the grid
because I've been so preoccupied.
I didn't notice
she was an entirely different person
and now a Batman supervillain
just kicked all of our asses.
So, yeah, the thought of blowing up
in a fiery explosion
honestly sounds like a vacation
to me...
Maybe that will get you
out of your head.
Where are you going?
To look for my damn car.
Okay then.
A friend of mine told me
this worked for her
so I figured, what the hell.
Look, Dad...
I get why you don't think
I'm ready to be Batwing.
Because you and I
and a whole lot of O.R. doctors
know that I'm not even supposed
to be here right now.
I'm supposed to be on ground
next to you
with a severed vein
and three ruptured organs.
But thanks to some lucky,
impossible, freak miracle, I'm not.
I'm still here.
But what if...
what if it wasn't a freak miracle?
What if your death
wasn't a tragedy?
What if all these horrible things
that happened to me
happened for a reason?
Because that's what
I'm trying to think.
And...
as hard as it is to say...
I can't keep caring
about what you would think
because, Dad, I'm ready.
And I love you and I miss you but...
I can't let you hold me back anymore.
You father would be proud of you.
Sorry, man.
I tried but I can't get it open.
Oh, damn it.
Got that same line from ARGUS.
Figured I had a fighting chance
with your Bat tech.
To be honest,
I don't actually have access
to our best resources
at the moment.
But from what I can tell,
the technology used
on a "Transmatter Cube"
probably
isn't from around here, is it?
Which is why I'd appreciate you
keeping this between us.
How did you get it open last time?
That's the problem.
I didn't do anything.
It just opened for me.
So maybe the key to opening that box
isn't based on science,
human or otherwise.
Maybe it's something else entirely.
Yeah.
I need you to do one more favor
for me.
- Okay. What's that?
- Get a message to Batwoman.
Let her know that
Jada Jet found a fix.
She's ready to save her son.
Since when is it day?
What happened to you girl?
Get away from me.
Dad!
Oh, little sister,
what have you done?
Let's just call this what it is.
A toxic relationship.
How are you here?
I, I...
Pheromone'd my ass?
I know, I was there.
When I thought there was a chance
I'd see you again, I created a toxin.
Started ingesting a drop a day
hoping to build up a tolerance
to your mind-control.
I guess you could say
I was afraid you'd do exactly
what you ended up doing.
You don't love me.
I do love you, Pam
I just don't love you
the way you want me to love you.
Then that's not love.
It's judgment.
Maybe this is a toxic relationship.
I've seen addicts
wean themselves off of heroin faster
than what we're doing to each other.
What do you think kept me alive
for 10 years, Renee?
I had no water, no sunlight...
no human contact.
I thought I was going to die there.
So what single thought do you think
I held onto for every waking moment
of every brutal day?
You.
So, if loving you through everything
we've been through
is toxic, then fine.
We're toxic.
Walk away.
But that doesn't mean
I'll ever let you go.
Your sporeling
is stronger than expected.
Are you gonna let me do this
or stand in our way?
You found me.
No.