Previously on Batwoman...
Marquis is sick.
There was an incident.
The Joker pressed
this godforsaken thing
to my son's head
and turned him into a monster.
I've been told that
another buzz could kill him.
I am losing my mind!
The hallucinations are back.
I just need a little edger
until you get me the Joy Buzzer.
There is only one buzz left.
Ryan needs it for her brother.
Your dad programmed your suit's AI
to speak with his voice?
- Dad, say hello to Mary.
- Hello, Mary.
It's like you can talk to him again.
It seems Batwoman is a no-show.
Oh, my God.
That's why Batwoman didn't show up.
She was here the whole time.
I'm sorry, Mary.
What did you do?
What if I were to give you
something that would make the Joker
wish he were you?
Let's have some fun.
Exactly where you said they would be,
funny man.
Oh, my God.
- What are you doing?
- Why isn't this stronger?
Alice, stop this.
A voltage and conductor.
They said it would work.
Why isn't it working?
- What are you doing?
- Getting Alice out of my head!
Alice, stop!
- That could kill you.
- Give it back!
Wait. Wait.
Just wait.
I told you I would help you.
I found a place.
It's in Switzerland.
It's near Geneva.
And it's called
the Weisse Kaninchen Sanatorium.
They specialize in childhood trauma.
They can help you.
No.
No more cells.
No more institutions.
I cannot be in my head anymore!
I want out!
Please, get me out of here.
I can't... Please.
Please.
All right, Batwoman, what's the plan?
How do we best handle
our one wild and precious buzz?
Marquis showed us
he doesn't have access
to a sliver of humanity
and, thanks to Alice,
he just got control of the Batcave
so however we get him,
it's gotta be today.
And if this thing only has juice
for one buzz
I have to be the one
to make the play.
So we lure him close and I hit him
before he knows what's coming.
Or, alternatively,
we give it to Alice.
Sorry I'm late.
You know she just gave Marquis
the keys to the bat kingdom, right?
I just came from Arkham
where I found her playing
DIY electroshock therapy
with a socket wrench.
She's not gonna survive
her next psychological break.
We tried to help her.
Alice made her bed.
Okay, Mary.
We know you feel
a certain whatever for her
but the buzzer created Marquis.
The Joker created Marquis.
And if we're splitting hairs,
he created Alice too.
Alice killed your mom, Mary.
You think I forgot?
You think I don't know how badly
Ryan wants her brother back?
Or that the first time
Alice ever met Sophie
she threw her
off a 30-story building?
I know.
It is not like this is some
easy decision for me
or anyone.
But I believe
Alice is capable of change.
She just needs a chance.
Each one of you looked me
in the eye a few weeks ago
apologized for sidelining me
and assured me I would have
a voice on this team.
This is it.
This is me using my voice.
This is... This is what I want.
I need to save Alice's life.
I just got a live urgent message
from Marquis Jet.
- Me too.
- I think we all did.
What's up, Gotham City?
We having fun yet?
Marquis Jet hollering at you
from a top secret location.
The time has come, the day is here,
tonight is the damn night.
I need everyone
to take to the streets.
Get out on your balconies,
jump up on your car
hell, climb to the tippy top
of your corner church steeple
because in five hours on the dot...
I'm gonna be shouting
Batwoman's true identity
from the rooftops.
Spoiler alert.
She's not the hero you think she is.
Ticktock, Gotham.
This is really happening.
Marquis Jet is about to shut
Batwoman down for good.
We are still hours away
from the Batwoman name drop
but curiosity has already pulled
some Gotham residents
to the streets
reacting to claims made
by Wayne CEO Marquis Jet
that he knows
the Scarlet Knight's secret identity
and that we should all
brace for disappointment.
No details beyond that were teased
but putting a face to the name
would certainly be the end
of business as usual
for the caped crusader
whose anonymity
is key to her own safety
and those of her loved ones.
While various theories
surrounding who's behind the mask
has been bouncing around
social media...
- Guys?
- Told you she doesn't knock.
I take it you saw Marquis's threat?
I believe 10 million people
saw Marquis's threat.
How on earth did he hijack
every phone, TV, and livestream
in this city?
He got into the Batcave.
From there, he found the computer
which led to Wayne's satellite
which he used to override
Gotham's airwaves.
My dad created the tech
in the event that
Batman had to send an SOS
to every person in the city
all at once.
Any chance
you can trace the original feed
back to its location?
Without access to The Batcave
I was lucky to be able
to get a screen cap.
Well, that's not gonna help us.
What are you doing?
Do you remember how your father
always repeated himself
- when he got mad?
- Vividly.
- Why?
- I can hear him now.
"Jada...
You let my boy take on Marquis
with a smartphone and a dial-up?"
I'm sure my tech team can pull
a carrier-grade router
off Jeturian's server farm.
Thank you?
We don't have a lot of time.
We've got to find Marquis
and buzz him with that Joy Buzzer.
Where's Ryan?
That is such a good question.
Right.
Sophie, didn't Ryan tell you
where she was headed?
Yes. I believe she said
she was running an errand.
- An errand.
- Right. That's what I remember.
Duh, she did mention that errand.
Where was it again?
Tell me why you deserve
the Joy Buzzer.
Shouldn't you be out
enjoying your last few hours
of superhero anonymity?
Yeah, I should.
Instead, I'm here
doing my best friend a solid
while the person
who actually needs it
is out there threatening to destroy
everything I've worked for.
Oh, you mean the brother
you're scared is too good to be true?
Face it, Ry-Ry.
You can blame Mary all you want
but deep down
in that little orphan heart
you need me to have that thing.
Oh, wow, Mary was right.
You did stop making sense.
Or...
chances are
you've spent the last few months
daydreaming about what it might
be like to have a nuclear family.
Thanksgiving dinners,
family game nights...
the comfort of a kidney,
should a new one become necessary.
Your desperation is showing.
What if you zap Marquis
and that good little boy
buried beneath that tacky clown suit
turns out to be doing just fine
without his needy little sister?
Do you really want to risk
getting your hopes up
only to have him leave you
like everybody else?
I'm your safe bet, Ryan.
Psycho or sane,
you don't need me to love you back.
Our Stingrays
can simulate a cell tower.
And since our supercomputers are
too big to walk through that door
you'll need this.
A secure access point
to the quantum computer
at Gotham University.
Did you say "quantum computer"?
Your father had me fund
the computer lab it lives in.
It seems only right you use it.
Greg, tell Hershel to pull
the generator into the alley.
This processor makes the Batcave
look like it runs on a hamster wheel.
Where were all of these resources
when Jada didn't think
we had the Joy Buzzer?
Dibs on not being the one
to tell her.
Any update from Ryan?
Not yet.
So, what's it gonna be, Ry-Ry?
Well...
This was a waste of my time.
Have a nice life, Alice.
I don't deserve the Joy Buzzer, okay?
We both know
that's what you wanted to hear.
But I do have
a little piece of information
you're gonna need
if you wanna live to see tomorrow.
What are you talking about?
Dare I say
it's accurate to assume that
Marquis is harboring a...
wee little man crush on the Joker?
We got a hit.
Honing in on Marquis's location now.
- How does that make sense?
- Where are all of those?
His singular cell ID is pinging off
ten different shops in Gotham Square.
According to your brother,
when he was 7
the Joker jumped on his bus
and whispered his big evil plan
to destroy Gotham City
once and for all.
Unfortunately for the Joker
Batty stopped him
and dumped him in Arkham
before he could pull it off, but...
Curious Cathy over here
wandered down to the caf
and asked a few of the Arkham lifers
if Mr. Smiley Pants had ever
talked about what he had
planned on doing that day.
Did I ever hear
the most interesting riddle.
He's moving.
Just really, really slow.
Converting coordinates,
adding altitude...
He's not on the ground.
He's in the air.
So, what, Marquis took the Wayne jet?
Well, if the Wayne jet
moved that slow
it would fall out of the sky.
- No.
- What?
No, no, no. No.
What was it?
"Tease them with a riddle,
get them all outside.
What's wet and melts and isn't snow
but ends in genocide?"
This isn't about my identity, is it?
That was just the draw.
This is about the Joker's desire
to punish the city
for worshipping the Bat symbol.
It's about killing as many people
as humanly possible
and riddling this city with survivors
that are as ugly as him.
How?
How does one person blow up
an entire city?
He took it. It's gone.
He... He must've found
the location of the secret airstrip
in the Batcave's records.
What do you mean it's gone?
What's gone?
The Bat-Blimp.
The game's changed.
This isn't about my identity.
It's about luring 10 million
innocent people to their deaths.
In one hour, Marquis is dropping
acid bombs over the city
and destroying everything
and everyone in its blast radius.
So we may be in a bar
dealing with the fallout
of Batman's greatest enemy
without a Joy Buzzer
or time to think straight
but we don't get excuses.
No one dies today, am I clear?
- Crystal.
- Good.
Any chance you can hack into
the controls of the Bat-Blimp?
I've never once seen
the Blimp's interface
but it's possible the coordinates
are vulnerable to an IMSI-catcher.
- Need a yes or no.
- I can't land it
- but I can probably get it close.
- Close is all we need.
I need you to direct it
to the GCPD rooftop.
Why? What are you planning?
So you can stop me?
It's that crazy?
Look at you figuring me out already.
No time for details.
Besides, I need you and Mary
to put your brains together
to get everyone in the city
to take cover
without inciting a chaos mob.
How? Not to throw shade
on my own sex appeal here
but you know I only have, like,
300 followers on socials, right?
The Batman Trophies.
Chances are Marquis cleaned house
on the Bat weapons
but he doesn't have access
to the wing with the trophy room
- without Batwoman's DNA.
- So?
So, between the Mad Hatter's hat
and the Condiment King's gun
surely there's some kooky tool
in there
that can influence people's behavior.
Okay, let's say there were.
How the hell
do we get into the Batcave?
I'm sure Marquis quadrupled security
since Batwing and I got busted
breaking into Wayne.
Jada's really not happy with me,
but I may have an idea.
I'm sorry.
When you said
we'd get our family back
I trusted you.
- We will get our family back.
- How?
That buzzer was the only way
to save Marquis.
You knew that,
and you still gave it away.
Having that buzzer in our possession
wouldn't change the fact that
a blimp hovering over our city
is about to douse our streets
with the Joker's acid bombs.
We need to get people to safety.
I have connections, Ryan
but I highly doubt
the President of the United States
is going to take my call...
I don't need the President.
I need my mom.
To pick up her phone and get me
Wayne Enterprises back.
Do to him what you did to me.
If it were that simple,
I would have done it weeks ago.
Marquis is smart.
His accounting is bulletproof.
And I'm guessing he's not hiding
a billion-dollar vigilante fund.
No.
But he is hiding something.
The ugly truth.
Jada, if you do mean
what I think you mean
there could be serious ramifications
for you too.
I've risked everything
to protect my son and failed.
It's time I take a page
from my daughter's handbook.
It's time to put the city first.
It's never good when your CFO
calls you at martini o'clock.
Yeah?
Who said that?
You think you can fire me?
You and who else?
Oh, the DOJ.
That's rich.
Yeah, have fun with that.
Marquis Jet's own mother,
business tycoon Jada Jet
just admitted
to the decades-long family secret.
Three years ago,
Franklin Jet was pronounced dead
after a fall.
These allegations
now throw that into question.
Meanwhile, the Wayne board has
unanimously reappointed Ryan Wilder
to the CEO position
calling her previous resignation
"coerced".
That position
would be reinstated immediately.
Ms. W...
You think I care about Wayne?
Or family?
Or any of you idiots?
Don't you get it?
None of you matter anymore.
Luke, we're in. Jada's play worked.
Wayne Tower was post-apocalyptic.
So, ready to teach me how to do this?
Luke? Hello?
- Batcave to Luke.
- Yep, I copy.
Just furiously hacking into a nuclear
Bat-Blimp from a bar stool.
Apologies for the three-second delay.
Okay. I'm at the computer.
Tell me how Marquis
was able to hijack the airwaves.
Okay, are you looking at
the satellite access portal?
The thing with the dots
and the numbers?
Let's assume yes.
So you're going to get a prompt
then you need to claim access
to each of the satellites.
Just click the box
next to the satellite file.
Okay. Clicking boxes...
It's kind of creepy how easy this is.
Well, considering
I just had to remind you
where the power switch was...
Okay, team doctor, not the techie.
I'd like to see
one of your patient intake reports.
I missed this.
What, me fumbling over
this electronic paperweight
you call a computer?
Us.
Me too.
Okay, I'm two clicks away
from controlling Gotham's airwaves.
Okay, cool. What did Sophie land on?
The Penguin's umbrella.
Inducing Gotham into a hypnotic state
via eye fascination.
I mean, that... That's brilliant.
Okay. Hey, get your hypno on.
I just got into the blimp.
Bat Bar to Batwoman.
Just landed.
All right, I'm in.
I'm entering your coordinates now.
Let me know when you see it.
Yeah.
Got eyes.
I love you morons.
What the hell was that?
Hey. Hey!
Why did we drop?
I have no idea, Mr. Jet.
The computer changed coordinates
then locked me out.
- Then put it in auto-pilot.
- I did.
Nothing is working, sir.
It's totally dead.
Guess you two have that in common.
Luke, I need this thing
to be a lot lower.
Yeah, trying. Something happened.
I'm literally staring
at a ticking clock here.
Yeah, I lost access.
Everything just dropped offline.
I need some time to get back in.
We don't have time.
Wish me luck.
Whoa, whoa, hey, hey,
what are you doing?
Taking the scenic route.
Lord, help me.
I'm in the cargo hold now.
What do you see?
Please tell me they taught you
how to disarm a bomb at Point Rock.
Give me eyes on it.
Half a dozen drums...
all attached to a timer that tells me
we have less than 15 minutes
before Marquis makes it rain acid
all over Gotham.
Where do I start?
You don't.
Okay, I was expecting something
more like cut the green or purple.
I count at least four trip wires
that would set this off early.
Not to mention
any other nasty hidden surprises
the Joker might have left behind.
You touch any one of those wires,
the whole damn thing could go.
Where the hell are we
with the evac-ing the city?
Just about to access
the Wayne security mainframe
and drop a hot tip now.
Get underground immediately.
Take cover. Wait for instructions.
Oh, my God, it's working.
Penguin's umbrella is actually
hypnotizing people to take cover.
You hear that, Batwoman?
We're making progress.
You out of there yet?
I'm gonna try to reroute the blimp
over the ocean.
Okay.
Tell me you learned how to wire
a blimp's controls at Point Rock.
Pretty sure
"pilot a giant combustible balloon"
wasn't offered in basic training.
This thing blows, the acid's still
gonna rain down over the city.
Once Marquis realizes
we took away his audience
he could trigger the bomb
at any moment with you still inside.
I can't just walk away from this.
I'm not losing you, Ryan.
You don't get to play
the crazy card with me.
I'm not losing you.
Nobody's ever said that to me before.
And nobody ever will again.
Should've known
you had something to do
with what's going on below.
See, this is why
I never wanted a little sister.
They ruin all the fun.
Your definition of fun
is blowing up half of Gotham?
Oh, why so pessimistic?
That means half the island lives
to remember the day
that the Bat-Blimp disfigured them
beyond recognition
and Batwoman didn't save them.
Disarm the bomb.
Everyone's taken cover already.
- Your plan failed.
- No, your plan failed.
Your plan to weasel into my life
and steal Mommy away?
- Hard fail, sis.
- Disarm the bomb, Marquis.
What is this,
your last attempt to win Jada's love?
You save her screwed-up son
and then maybe she'll apologize
for leaving you in a drop box?
She doesn't love you, Wilder.
Take the hint.
I'm not doing this for Jada.
Right, the hero's burden. I forgot.
You're doing this for mankind.
I'm doing it for my family.
Give me my brother back!
Give him back!
Please. I want Marquis. Please!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry
that you're so desperate for a family
that you believed you could save me.
Batwoman?
Ryan?
Ryan, are you there? Check in.
Ryan? Ryan, talk to me.
Please say something. Are you okay?
You think I'm gonna die
before you buy me dinner?
- The bomb.
- We're on it.
It's worse than I thought.
Can you rewire the controls?
Not in two minutes.
I'd need to install
a whole new operating system
to steer this thing out of the city.
But you're Luke.
There's always
some super genius gigabyte-filled
rabbit in a hat somewhere, right?
Right.
You're right.
My helmet's AI.
Okay. It can do that?
Well, my dad designed the Bat-Tech
to talk to each other.
The AI is the only thing that can
override this nav system in time.
If I can dock it to the mainframe
we might actually have
a fighting chance.
Wait, dock it? As in leave it behind?
Only way this works.
But, Luke, that's your dad.
Sophie.
Give me a direction I can get to
in 2 minutes and 15 seconds.
Copy. I'm on it.
Do bats have nine lives too?
Because I don't think
you can hold us up much longer.
You willing to kill me
or die for me, sis?
I'm not letting go.
Is it just me
or is this evil plan
unfolding exactly as I called it?
Look at me doing something
out of the goodness of my heart.
Surprised you didn't
spontaneously burst into flames.
Must mean I've really changed.
Did this earn me the buzzer or what?
You're really willing
to ditch the bitch.
I watched my mom's head
bobbing down a river.
I endured a life sentence
in a monster's basement
and had my head scrambled
by a woman scorned.
And now,
I'm coming to you of all people
for some magic key
to make the crazy go poof.
That must show you
how desperate I am.
I don't see desperate.
I see a girl who lived a hell of life
capable of change.
I can't do it on my own.
No, you don't want to do it
on your own.
Because it's hard.
But if anyone can survive hard,
Alice, it's you.
This is for Mary
but deep down, Mary knows
and I know and you know
you are not the one who needs this.
Thank you. I mean it.
To be clear, we still aren't friends.
And I can't help you with that.
Okay. Less than a minute, Batwing.
How much longer
before it's operational?
AI's in. I just need coordinates.
Sophie, now.
These calculations were made
when we still had two minutes
on the clock.
What do you mean?
We don't have time
to get it out of Gotham?
Batcave, I need a direction ASAP.
Twenty seconds.
Sophie, coordinates!
Okay, 40 degrees north,
73 degrees west.
If we can't get it to the ocean
we can at least get it
to the city's most desolate area.
It's working. Now get out of there.
You inspired me to be a hero.
Thanks, Dad.
I'm proud of you son.
You and your team
will save a lot of lives tonight.
Now go save yours.
Batcave to Batwing. Do you read?
Batwing, check in. Are you okay?
I'm here.
I got out of there.
Hello?
Hey, what are you doing out here?
I got split up from my mom.
I don't know where she went.
Okay. I'll help you find her.
Who are you anyway?
Call me Batwing.
How is he?
His vitals are stable.
Physically, he's okay.
But until he wakes up,
we won't know if the buzzer worked.
It's going to work.
Thank you for finding a way
to make this happen.
I told you, you can trust me.
Ryan.
Despite my mistakes,
you have exceeded my wildest dreams.
I can't change the past, but...
maybe we can build
a different future.
I'd like that.
Marquis?
Baby, can you hear me?
Hi, Mom.
Hey, sis.
Nice to meet you for real.
You have no idea.
How do you feel?
Like I need my little sister.
Seriously?
Good for you, Beth.
So, what next?
Well, now that we've got Wayne back,
what's next is reclaiming this space
as in what is up
with that tacky ass TV
covering my stained glass?
I mean, what's next for us?
Well, I thought we agreed
you were gonna buy me dinner.
Brought the champ.
And we're interrupting.
This is gonna keep happening,
isn't it?
- Probably.
Well, I for one am not gonna let
a slightly awkward sensation
get in the way of our rare
opportunity to celebrate.
I'm actually glad you're all here.
I need your help
getting this place right again.
Starting with this.
That's better.
So, do I wanna know
what he did to our Batcave?
Doesn't Batwoman take a night of?
This is Gotham.
Home of infectious reptile teeth
dudes in pig masks
a killer vine causing my bestie
to get her baddie on.
If I have learned anything
it is to be prepared for everything
at all times.
- Are y'all with me?
- We're with you, Batwoman.
Where else would we be?
Yup.
Oh, I thought we were drinking.
You know what, you're right.
I'm just... I'll bring it.
I'll take it with.
Let's get to work.
This is Dana Dewitt,
live from the toxic scene
that could've destroyed Gotham City
without the heroics of Batwoman.
The city has advised citizens
to stay away from the area
as they assess
the hazardous air quality
caused by the Joker's acid bomb
that blanketed the neighbor...
Oh, my God. What is that?
- Oh, my God!
- No...