PREVIOUSLY ON BATWOMAN...
I'M POISON IVY.
I NEARLY KILLED SOMEONE,
AND I DON'T KNOW WHY
OR WHEN THIS INFECTION
IS GONNA MAKE ME
TRANSFORM AGAIN.
MARQUIS IS SICK.
THERE WAS... AN INCIDENT.
THE JOKER HAD THIS
ZAPPER ON HIS HAND.
HE PRESSED IT AGAINST
MY SON'S FOREHEAD.
AFTER THAT DAY,
HE WAS DIFFERENT, DARK,
HORRIFYING.
YOU FIGURED OUT SUNLIGHT
WAS MY TRIGGER.
- UNH!
- AAH!
DAD, HELP! HELP ME!
YOUR DAD'S GONE, LUKE.
I TOOK OUT YOUR FAILSAFE.
WHAT UP, SIS?
READY TO BLOW UP THE
GOTHAM BUSINESS WORLD?
WELL, WE GOT TO MAKE UP
FOR SKIPPING
THAT REBELLIOUS TEEN PHASE.
GUESS THIS IS WHAT
IT WOULD HAVE FELT LIKE
SNEAKING OUT OF THE HOUSE
UNDER JADA'S NOSE.
YEAH, BUT INSTEAD OF SMOKING
BLUNTS IN THE POOL HOUSE,
WE'RE PLANNING A CORPORATE
MERGER BEHIND HER BACK,
A TRUE FAMILY BUSINESS.
SO HOW DO YOU PROPOSE
WE MAKE THIS HAPPEN
IF YOU DON'T THINK
JADA WILL EVER GO FOR IT?
WELL, THE FIRST THING
THAT WE GOT TO DO
IS PROPOSE A PLAN
THAT EVERYONE LOVES,
THEN USE THE ELEMENT
OF SURPRISE.
♪ I AIN'T PLAYING
'CAUSE LIFE AIN'T KIND ♪
♪ VICTORY, VICTORY'S MINE
♪ I AIN'T PLAYING
'CAUSE LIFE AIN'T KIND ♪
♪ VICTORY, VICTORY'S MINE
WHOA, WHOA.
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
- YO. WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- SORRY, MARQUIS.
♪ PLAY TO WIN OR NOT
♪ HEAD SHOT, YOU SOLD OUT ♪
WHAT'S... WHAT'S GOING ON?
♪ I DEMAND THEM NOW ON SIGHT ♪
♪ CHECKING MY INTENSITY,
AND I'M ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ IF YOU GOT A BOSS,
GUESS HE'LL BE FINE ♪
♪ ONE OF YOU LOT
CAN HIT REVIVE ♪
MOM, I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
IT'S FOR YOUR OWN GOOD, BABY.
- TAKE HIM.
- YES, MA'AM.
♪ DON'T LIKE IT,
DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT ♪
♪ I AIN'T PLAYING
'CAUSE LIFE AIN'T KIND ♪
♪ VICTORY, VICTORY'S MINE
♪ DON'T LIKE IT,
DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT ♪
♪ I AIN'T PLAYING
'CAUSE LIFE AIN'T KIND ♪
♪ VICTORY, VICTORY'S MINE
YOU TOOK CARE OF YOUR FAMILY,
AND NOW YOUR FAMILY
WILL TAKE CARE OF YOU.
TELL ME MORE
ABOUT THIS FAVOR YOU NEED.
LEAVES OF 3, STAY AWAY FROM ME.
GOTHAM'S BOTANICAL GARDEN
WAS THE SITE
OF SOME HORTICULTURAL HIJINKS
THAT SOURCES SAY
BEAR A STRIKING RESEMBLANCE
TO THOSE
OF GOTHAM SUPERVILLAIN
POISON IVY.
THE TOXIC TROUBLEMAKER
OTHERWISE KNOWN AS PAMELA ISLEY
HASN'T BEEN SEEN
IN OVER A DECADE,
BUT JUDGING BY THE SIZE
OF THE VINES FOUND AT THE SCENE,
AUTHORITIES CAN'T HELP
BUT WONDER IF THERE'S
SOME OTHER ROOT CAUSE,
OR DOES GOTHAM NEED TO
BREAK OUT ITS CALAMINE?
♪ THAT MUCH TO ME
♪ DA DA DA DA DA DA DA
♪ DA DA DA DA DA DA DA DA ♪
♪ DA DA DA DA DA DA
♪ YOU'VE BEEN UP ON YOUR LUCK
♪ I'VE BEEN CHASING THE SUN
♪ YOU'VE BEEN LIVING THE DREAM
♪ SILENT WISHING MACHINE
♪ YOU'VE UP ON YOUR LUCK
♪ I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR LOVE
♪ I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR LOVE ♪
♪ IT DON'T MEAN
THAT MUCH TO ME ♪
♪ DA DA DA DA DA DA DA
♪ DA DA DA DA DA DA DA ♪
MARY IS POISON IVY?
WELL THAT DEPENDS.
SHE'S KIND OF GOT
A JEKYLL AND HYDE
THING GOING ON,
SO AT NIGHTTIME SHE'S FINE,
BUT WHEN THE SUN COMES UP,
THE SWEET AND LOVING
MARY THAT WE KNOW
TAKES A BACKSEAT TO A
VEGETATION-WIELDING SUPERVILLAIN.
I'M GUESSING MARY'S
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR ARM.
YEAH. SHE MADE
HER POINT VERY CLEAR
THAT SHE DOESN'T WANT
ME SUITING UP.
SHE ALSO TRIED TO SQUEEZE
THE LIFE OUT OF BATWOMAN.
NO ONE'S SEEN HER SINCE.
IS THERE A WAY TO CURE HER?
NOT YET, BUT THERE WILL BE.
THERE WILL? HOW EXACTLY?
JADA HAS THE BEST MINDS
AT JETURIAN ON IT.
I GAVE THEM A SAMPLE
OF MARY'S BLOOD.
THEY'RE TRYING TO
SYNTHESIZE AN ANTIDOTE.
YOUR MOM DOESN'T REALLY
DO ALTRUISM,
SO WHAT'S IN IT FOR HER?
HOW LONG BEFORE WE CAN
BEGIN THE FREEZING PROCESS?
AS SOON AS MY TECHS CAN FLUSH
HIS SYSTEM OF ANY INTOXICANTS
OR OTHER CONTRAINDICATIONS.
PLACING A HUMAN
IN SUSPENDED ANIMATION
IS UNCHARTED TERRITORY.
WE DON'T WANT TO RUSH THINGS.
THEN THAT SHOULD GIVE YOU
THE TIME TO FOCUS
ON OUR OTHER PROJECT.
WHERE ARE WE WITH THAT?
WELL, NO ONE HAS SEEN A
PLANT-BASED INFECTION LIKE THIS
SINCE SWAMP THING.
BUT YOU CAN ERADICATE IT.
WE'RE SYNTHESIZING
THE ANTIDOTE NOW.
SORRY I DIDN'T
SAY ANYTHING BEFORE,
BUT I COULDN'T SAY ANYTHING
UNTIL MARQUIS WAS IN CUSTODY.
YOU DIDN'T
HAVE TO DO THIS ALONE.
I COULD HAVE HELPED YOU.
HE IS UNSTABLE AND DANGEROUS.
I COULDN'T RISK PUTTING
ANYBODY ELSE IN JEOPARDY.
- I GET IT.
- WELL, I DON'T.
SO YOUR MOM GOT WHAT SHE WANTED,
AND YOU REALLY JUST TRUST
THAT SHE'S GOING TO DELIVER
ON A CURE FOR MARY?
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH CHOICE.
JADA'S PEOPLE TESTED
MARY'S BLOOD.
THEY BELIEVE THE INFECTION'S
DOUBLING EVERY 12 HOURS.
AT THAT RATE,
THIS MIGHT BE THE LAST NIGHT
SHE'S STILL MARY.
- WHERE IS SHE NOW?
- I RAN FACIAL RECOGNITION SWEEP
OF EVERY CAMERA IN GOTHAM,
BUT NO PHONE SIGNAL,
NO CREDIT CARD ACTIVITY.
HERE'S TO HOPING THAT
WHEN THE SUN GOES DOWN
SHE'LL CALL US.
IS THAT A HIT ON MARY?
NO. IT'S ALICE.
HER TRACKER SAYS
THAT SHE BREACHED
HER 15-MILE PERIMETER,
SO SHE'S OFF LEASH
AND HAULING ASS
OUT OF GOTHAM.
YOUR ROOMMATE HAPPEN
TO TELL WHERE SHE WAS
GOING THIS MORNING?
I DIDN'T EXACTLY
GO HOME LAST NIGHT.
GREAT. SO... MARY'S IN THE WIND,
AND NOW ALICE IS
MAKING A RUN FOR IT.
YOU DON'T THINK MARY IS
WITH ALICE, DO YOU?
♪ HEY, HOT BETTY,
DO YOU WANT TO DANCE? ♪
WILL YOU TAKE A CHANCE? ♪
♪ BRING IT RIGHT TO ME
IN YOUR DIRTY PANTS ♪
♪ HEY, HOT BETTY,
DO YOU WANT TO DANCE? ♪
GET ON THE FLOOR ♪
WHY ARE WE IN A MOTOR HOME?
OH. BECAUSE WE WRECKED
OUR SUPERSEXY SPORTS CAR
FLEEING THE GCPD.
ALICE, WHAT DID YOU DO?
ACTUALLY, IT'S NOT WHAT I DID
BUT, UH, IF YOU DON'T REMEMBER,
IT'S PROBABLY FOR THE BEST.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO LISTEN TO?
IT'S YOUR TURN
TO CHANGE THE STATION.
ALICE, STOP.
FINE.
BUT WE WERE MAKING
REALLY GOOD TIME.
I NEED TO CALL RYAN AND LUKE.
WHERE'S MY PHONE?
OH, YOU THREW IT
INTO THE GOTHAM RIVER
ON OUR WAY OUT.
YOUR IDEA. BESIDES,
YOU MIGHT WANT TO LET
RY-RY AND HER LITTLE SIDEKICK
COOL OFF A LITTLE BIT.
THEY'RE BOUND TO BE SORE
FIGURATIVELY
AND, UM, THE OTHER WAY.
IS THIS LUKE'S BATWING AI?
OH, YEAH. APPARENTLY, YOU
JUST RIPPED IT RIGHT OFF
AND ALMOST TOOK
HIS ARM ALONG WITH IT.
I SINCERELY HOPE HE'S
NOT LEFT-HANDED.
BUT DON'T WORRY.
IT'S NOT NEARLY AS BAD
AS WHAT YOU DID TO RYAN.
OH, GOD. I'M GONNA BE SICK.
OH. WELL, YOU'RE IN LUCK.
OUR NEW RIDE HAS A TOILET.
TRUST ME, SISTER.
IT'S NICER THAN THE ONE
IN ARKHAM.
RYAN AND LUKE WOULD NEVER
PUT ME IN THERE.
WELL, IT'S NOT LIKE YOU
GAVE THEM MUCH OF A CHOICE.
I MEAN, YOU DID TRY
TO KILL THEM,
AND AS FOR RENEE MONTOYA
FINDING OUT ABOUT YOU,
WELL, LET'S JUST SAY THAT
CACTUS IS OUT OF THE BAG.
I'M GONNA BE A FUGITIVE
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
NO.
JUST UNTIL YOU LEARN
TO CONTROL YOUR POWERS,
AND I'M HAPPY TO KEEP
YOU SAFE UNTIL THEN.
UHH. JUST OUT OF THE
KINDNESS OF YOUR HEART?
IT'S FUNNY YOU SHOULD
MENTION MY HEART ACTUALLY.
CURRENTLY, I HAVE THOUSANDS
OF CREEPY NANOBOTS RUNNING
THROUGH MY BLOODSTREAM,
SENDING OUT ANNOYING
LITTLE TRACKING SIGNALS,
AND IF THEY CAN FIND ME,
WELL... THEY CAN FIND YOU.
THOUGH YOU WOULDN'T
HAPPEN TO KNOW A DOCTOR
WHO COULD DO A FULL BLOOD
TRANSFUSION, WOULD YOU?
BUT THEN YOU'D GO FREE.
SOMETIMES, YOU NEED TO
PICK YOUR POISON, DEAR.
WHO DO YOU TRUST MORE
RIGHT NOW...
YOUR FRIENDS, WHO WILL
SURELY LOCK YOU AWAY,
OR YOUR SISTER, WHO'S
TRYING TO KEEP YOU FREE?
WHAT'S YOUR TYPE?
TALL, DARK, AND BROODING.
YOUR BLOOD TYPE.
O NEGATIVE.
LUKE, ON COMMS: YOU'RE ABOUT
HALF A MILE FROM ALICE
WEST ON I-15.
OH, THAT'S WEIRD.
UM, SORRY. SIGNAL'S GLITCHY.
LET ME JUST WIDEN OUT,
SEE IF I CAN GET A BETTER LOOK.
UH-OH.
NOT LIKING THE SOUND
OF THAT "UH-OH."
TALK TO ME, LUKE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
UH, ACTUALLY, I HAVE
ANOTHER TRACKER GOING EAST NOW.
HOW THE HELL IS SHE
GOING EAST AND WEST?
NO, WAIT. UH, NOW I HAVE
ONE GOING NORTH.
I'VE GOT ALICES POPPING UP
ALL OVER THE MAP.
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON?
ONLY ONE WAY TO FIND OUT.
WHOA. BATWOMAN? WHAT DID I DO?
OH. I'M A BIG FAN.
PLEASE DON'T HURT ME.
OPEN THE TRUNK.
NO SIGN OF ALICE OR MARY.
OK. WELL, I GOT ABOUT
20 OF THEM HERE,
AND THEY'RE SCATTERING
IN ALL DIFFERENT DIRECTIONS.
I... I DON'T GET IT.
I DO. ALICE KNOWS
WE'RE TRACKING THE NANOBOTS
IN HER BLOOD,
SO SHE'S SPILLING IT
ON VEHICLES HEADING IN
EVERY DIRECTION ON THE MAP,
AND I KNOW WHY MARY
HASN'T CALLED US YET.
SHE'S WITH ALICE.
AND HOW WAS THE HOSPITAL?
NOT NEARLY AS SECURE
AS IT SHOULD BE.
I GOT IV TUBING,
BUTTERFLY NEEDLES,
BLOOD COLLECTION BAGS
BUT NO BLOOD.
AT LEAST THAT WAS LOCKED AWAY.
AND YET ONLY ONE
ICED CARAMEL LATTEÉ
THAT DOESN'T LOOK
BIG ENOUGH TO SHARE.
I NEED THE CAFFEINE, OK?
BEING TWO PEOPLE IS EXHAUSTING.
MMM. BEFORE YOU CALL ME
A SUCKY FUGITIVE,
I PAID IN CASH, AND I
DIDN'T USE MY REAL NAME.
OH. OK. WELL, GOOD WORK...
DAPHNE.
NOW I JUST NEED TO FIND A DONOR.
HONESTLY, I'M NOT PICKY.
ACTUALLY, PICKY IS EXACTLY
WHAT YOU NEED TO BE.
YOU'RE O NEGATIVE, WHICH MEANS
YOU'RE A UNIVERSAL DONOR,
BUT YOU CAN ONLY
RECEIVE O NEG BLOOD.
HMM. SO HOW DO WE FIND
THIS, UM, SPECIAL SOMEONE?
HEY.
YOU KNOW WHAT WOMEN FIND
SO ATTRACTIVE IN A GUY?
IT'S NOT MUSCLES
OR A BIG BANK ACCOUNT.
IT'S... O NEGATIVE BLOOD.
- BIG TURN-ON.
- MMM.
SHOULD WE DO A LITTLE CHECKSIES?
UH, I'M GOOD.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THE HELL'S GOING ON HERE,
BUT YOU TWO ARE FREAKING OUT
OUR CUSTOMERS
WITH YOUR VAMPIRE KINK
OR WHATEVER IT IS YOU'RE INTO.
YOU GOT TO TAKE IT
OUT OF HERE NOW!
UHH. SORRY. YOU'RE KICKING
US OUT OF THIS PLACE
SIMPLY BECAUSE WE'RE
TRYING TO EDUCATE PEOPLE
ON THE IMPORTANCE OF
KNOWING THEIR BLOOD TYPE?
YOU KNOW WHAT, MISS?
YOU'RE COMPLETELY RIGHT.
I AM SO SORRY.
STAY AS LONG AS YOU WANT.
THAT WAS WEIRD.
OH, MARE-BEAR.
IT'S ABOUT TO GET A LOT WEIDER.
I THINK SOMEONE'S MIND CONTROL
PHEROMONES JUST KICKED IN.
HOW IS THIS POSSIBLE?
IT'S NIGHT, AND I'M
DEFINITELY STILL MYSELF.
WELL, GET READY FOR THE
MAKEOVER OF A LIFETIME
BECAUSE THIS MAY JUST
BE STEP ONE
IN YOUR BLEND
TO FULL POISON MARY.
YOU DON'T BELIEVE ME?
TAKE ANOTHER STAB AT IT.
HEY.
CAN WE GET A BUNCH
OF SHOTS ON THE HOUSE?
YOU GOT IT.
SEE? PEOPLE ACTUALLY
LISTEN TO THIS MARY,
AND SHE GETS FREE STUFF.
I THINK I'M GONNA LIKE HER.
I JUST STOLE
FROM A SMALL BUSINESS,
AND I DON'T EVEN
FEEL BAD ABOUT IT.
YEAH.
WELCOME TO THE DARK SIDE.
AHH.
LUKE, WE DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH
LONGER MARY'S GONNA BE MARY.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET A LINE ON
WHICH TRACKER'S THE RIGHT ONE.
BLOOD CELLS CAN LIVE OUTSIDE OF
THE BODY FOR UP TO 4-6 HOURS.
WHEN THE BLOOD CELLS DIE OFF,
THE NANOBOTS WILL SHUT DOWN.
THAT'S THE PLAN? LITERALLY
WAIT FOR BLOOD TO DRY?
HOPEFULLY IT'LL BE BY SUN-UP
SO WE CAN GET TO MARY
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
HEY. NOT TO ADD TO OUR PROBLEMS,
BUT IF SHE GOES
FULL-BLOWN POISON IVY,
THE MAYOR HAS AUTHORIZED
EXTREME MEASURES.
AT THE TIME, I DIDN'T REALIZE
THEY WERE TALKING ABOUT MARY.
- WHO'S THEY?
- RENEE MONTOYA.
WHEN DID SHE TELL YOU THIS?
SO SHE'S THE REASON YOU
DIDN'T GO HOME LAST NIGHT.
YOU WERE WITH HER.
DIDN'T REALIZE I NEEDED
YOUR PERMISSION.
TO SLEEP WITH THE WOMAN
BLACKMAILING ME,
THREATENING ME WITH PRISON?
NO. OF COURSE NOT.
I AM SO HAPPY YOU TWO
FOUND EACH OTHER.
UH, JUST GOT WORD FROM JETURIAN.
- THE CURE'S READY.
- COPY.
LET'S GO.
MAMA...
MY HANDS STING.
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
YOU KNOW WHY, BABY.
EVER SINCE THE JOKER PRESSED
THAT BUZZER TO YOUR HEAD,
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN THE SAME.
IT WASN'T MY FAULT.
I KNOW...
AND I NEED TO FIX YOU
BEFORE SOMEONE THAT
DOESN'T UNDERSTAND THAT
TRIES TO PUT YOU AWAY FOR GOOD.
MAMA... I'M SORRY...
FOR EVERYTHING.
I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
JUST TRUST ME ON THIS.
HAVEN'T I ALWAYS
TAKEN CARE OF YOU?
WHEN YOU WAKE UP...
YOU'RE GONNA BE
MY MARQUIS AGAIN.
- AAH!
- RAAH!
AAH! UNH!
BACK OFF.
YOU WANT TO BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR KILLING JADA JET?
I WILL KILL HER.
HUH YAAH!
WHOA!
MARQUIS, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
DOING WHAT YOU TAUGHT ME.
TAKING INITIATIVE.
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED?
MARQUIS. HE ESCAPED.
- OH, MY GOD.
- HEY. TAKE IT EASY.
DON'T TRY TO GET UP.
I THOUGHT MARQUIS WAS ON ICE.
WE... WE FAILED.
WHERE COULD HE BE NOW?
RYAN...
HE WENT LOOKING FOR YOU.
NICE SLING.
MAKES YOU LOOK TOUGH.
IS RYAN AROUND?
I DON'T KNOW WHERE SHE IS.
- HOW DID YOU GET IN?
- AH. I TOLD THE STAFF
AT THE FRONT DESK
RYAN AND I WERE BLOOD.
HOO. 18-KARAT GOLD NIB,
SATIN LACQUER FINISH.
OOH! PRICEY.
- AND HEFTY, TOO.
- CAN YOU PUT THAT DOWN?
THAT WAS A GIFT FROM MY DAD.
AH. SHOULD HAVE FIGURED.
YOU KNOW, LUCIUS FOX
ALWAYS HAD THE BEST TASTE.
YOU KNOW, YOUR OLD MAN USED
TO COME BY OUR PLACE SOMETIMES
FOR MY MOM'S FAMOUS
MOSCOW MULE NIGHTS.
YEAH. WE'D SHOOT HOOPS
IN THE DRIVEWAY SOMETIMES.
- GOOD MAN.
- DUDE... GIVE ME THE PEN.
NO.
THERE A PROBLEM, MR. FOX?
YEAH. IS THERE A PROBLEM,
MR. FOX?
YOU CALLED SECURITY ON ME?
YEAH. YOU DON'T NEED
TO BE HERE RIGHT NOW.
ALL RIGHT. RELAX.
LUKE AND I WERE JUST CHILLING
WHILE I WAIT FOR MY SISTER.
YOU MIGHT KNOW HER AS YOUR BOSS.
PLEASE ESCORT MR. JET OUT.
UGH!
HERE'S YOUR PEN.
UNH!
THAT WAS A GOOD SHOT.
YOU'RE QUICK.
I WASN'T EVEN WARMED UP YET.
OHH! AAH! UGH! AGH!
♪ THESE ARE DESPERATE TIMES ♪
♪ AND DESPERATE MEASURES
ARE THE PRICE ♪
DON'T LIE TO YOURSELF.
YOU WOULDN'T BEAT ME
WITH TWO GOOD HANDS.
YOU READY TO WAVE
THE WHITE FLAG?
♪ I'MMA GET
REAL HIGH AND REAL LOW ♪
♪ LOSE YOUR MIND
♪ REAP WHAT YOU SOW
♪ UP IN SMOKE
♪ I'M A LITTLE BIT TWISTED
GOOD NIGHT.
YOU ARE SO AWESOME
TO CHECK MY BLOOD TYPE,
BUT WHY ARE
YOU CHECKING MY BLOOD TYPE?
BECAUSE IT'S IMPORTANT TO KNOW.
I MEAN, IMAGINE IF YOU WERE
IN A NEAR-FATAL ACCIDENT.
YOU WOULDN'T WANT TO
RUN THE RISK
OF BEING GIVEN THE WRONG BLOOD.
HEH. PLUS HOW ELSE WOULD
I BE ABLE TO FIND OUT
IF WE'RE COMPATIBLE?
OH, OK. THAT MAKES SENSE.
HMM.
IT'S AB NEGATIVE.
IT'S NOT GONNA CUT IT,
BUT THAT'S A VERY RARE
BLOOD TYPE, HIGH IN DEMAND.
YOU SHOULD REALLY CONSIDER
DONATING YOUR PLASMA.
I'LL GO FIND A PLACE
TO DONATE NOW. OK.
MARY, THIS IS JASON.
AHEM. JASON AND I
HAVE JUST BEEN TALKING
ABOUT HOW HARD IT IS
TO MEET PEOPLE
ORGANICALLY NOWADAYS.
JASON HAS NO PIERCINGS,
NO TATTOOS,
AND HE'S NEVER BEEN TO A COUNTRY
WHERE YOU CAN GET MALARIA.
PLUS BONUS. HE'S A GEMINI.
YOU SAID THERE WOULD BE WINGS.
OH. TSK, TSK, TSK.
THAT'S BAD FOR YOUR CHOLESTEROL.
PLACE YOUR HAND RIGHT HERE.
OH. NOW I WANT WINGS.
OHH! O NEG. WE HAVE A WINNER.
HA HA HA!
WHAT'D I WIN?
YOU GET TO DONATE 2... 3 PINTS
OF YOUR BLOOD
FOR A VERY GOOD CAUSE.
HA! I'M GONNA HAVE TO
CUT YOU OFF NOW.
DR. TUVA DIDN'T HAVE A SUBJECT
TO TEST THE ANTIDOTE ON,
BUT SHE'S CONFIDENT
THAT IT WILL WORK.
WELL, THAT MAKES ONE OF US.
I JUST HOPE THERE'S
STILL TIME TO SAVE MARY.
I KNOW YOU DON'T TRUST ME.
I'VE MADE A LOT OF MISTAKES,
BUT I ALWAYS KEEP MY PROMISES.
IT SHOULD BE IN HERE.
AAH!
MARQUIS...
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
OH! LUKE! LUKE?
CHILL. HE'S ALIVE. I CHECKED.
YOUR GUARD'S ANOTHER STORY.
YOUR FIGHT... IS WITH ME.
I'M THE ONE WHO BETRAYED YOU.
I GET WHY YOU'D BE UPSET.
I KNOW HOW AWFUL
THAT MUST HAVE FELT
TO HAVE YOUR SISTER
TURN AGAINST YOU.
HA HA HA! HA HA HA!
HA HA HA!
- WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
- HEH HEH. YOU.
YOU THOUGHT I WAS WOUNDED.
YOU THINK I'M ALL
TORN UP INSIDE.
OHH. MMM. SAD FACE BECAUSE
MY LONG LOST SISTER
STABBED ME IN THE BACK.
- MARQUIS.
- HEH HEH.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
PRETEND YOU'RE NOT HURT.
RYAN, WHAT, YOU DON'T GET IT?
THIS IS ME FINALLY
NOT PRETENDING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU BOUGHT INTO
THE WHOLE SIBLING BONDING CRAP.
YOU KNOW HOW HARD IT WAS FOR
ME TO KEEP A STRAIGHT FACE?
ME AND YOU
AGAINST THE WORLD, SIS.
HEH HEH HEH.
SO DESPERATE TO
CONNECT WITH THE FAMILY
THAT DIDN'T WANT YOU.
SEE, I WOULD HAVE
THOUGHT THAT YEARS
IN THE GROUP HOME WOULD
HAVE TOUGHENED YOU UP,
BUT YOU STILL FELL FOR IT.
HA HA HA! WAIT.
THE LOOK ON YOUR FACE RIGHT NOW,
IT MAKES IT ALL WORTH IT.
HOLD ON. LET ME TAKE A PICTURE.
USE THIS AS MY BACKGROUND.
- YOU'RE SICK.
- NOT AS SICK AS YOUR FRIEND.
YEAH. MOM FILLED ME IN YOUR LITTLE
DEAL BEFORE SHE BLACKED OUT.
NOT OFF THE RED WINE THIS TIME.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT THIS STUFF IS,
BUT BEING THAT YOU WOULD HAVE
SOLD OUT YOUR OWN BROTHER FOR IT,
I'M SURE IT'S IMPORTANT,
AND CONSIDERING THAT MOM'S
TEAM HAD A SUNRISE DEADLINE,
WELL, I'D SAY IT'S PRETTY
TIME-SENSITIVE, RIGHT?
OHH!
OK. HEH. OBVIOUSLY,
YOU HAVE A PRICE,
SO LET'S GET TO THE PART
WHERE YOU TELL ME WHAT IT IS
SINCE THE CLOCK IS TICKING.
ALL BUSINESS. YEAH. ME, TOO,
AND WHAT I WANT IS...
YOUR AUTOGRAPH
ON A RESIGNATION LETTER
OF YOU STEPPING DOWN AS CEO
OF WAYNE ENTERPRISES.
OH. I ALSO WANT ALL
YOUR STOCK OPTIONS.
OHH!
YOU'RE TRYING TO WAGE
A HOSTILE TAKEOVER.
YEAH, AND YOU'RE GONNA HELP ME
IF YOU WANT TO HELP YOUR FRIEND
IN A TIMELY FASHION,
AND I'D SAY YOU GOT
ABOUT AN HOUR
UNTIL SUNRISE.
OH. DO YOU NEED A PEN?
I REALLY WISH I WOULD HAVE GOTTEN
THE CHANCE TO KNOW THE REAL YOU
BEFORE THE JOKER DESTROYED YOU.
SEE? THAT'S THE THING.
IF THE JOKER WAS SO HORRIBLE,
WHY WAS HE THE ONLY ONE
IN THIS DAMN CITY
WHO LOOKED LIKE HE WAS
HAVING ANY FUN?
THANKS.
LUKE, I NEED A DIRECTION.
I'M ALL DRESSED UP
WITH NOWHERE TO GO.
UH, GOOD NEWS, BAD NEWS?
- BAD NEWS FIRST.
- OK.
MARY HASN'T USED
HER CREDIT CARDS
AND SHOCKINGLY
HASN'T POSTED ON INSTA,
SO I DON'T HAVE
A BEARING TO GIVE YOU,
AND WE ONLY HAVE 42
MINUTES UNTIL SUNRISE.
OK. YOU BETTER HIT ME
WITH THE GOOD NEWS.
19 OF OUR TRACKERS ARE OFFLINE,
- SO WE'RE DOWN TO 4.
- THAT'S THE GOOD NEWS?
I DIDN'T SAY IT WAS THAT GOOD.
SO YOU'VE GOT A 1 IN 4 CHANCE
OF PICKING THE RIGHT ONE.
OK. LET ME KNOW IF
ANY OF THE TRACKERS BLINK OUT.
LOOK. I'M NOT A DOCTOR,
AND AT POINT ROCK,
MY FIELD DRESSINGS
WERE FAMOUSLY TERRIBLE.
I'M JUST TRYING TO CHANNEL
WHAT MARY WOULD SAY HERE.
SHE'D TELL ME...
SHE'D TELL ME THAT THINGS
CAN'T HEAL UNLESS YOU LET THEM,
AND SHE'D BE RIGHT
JUST LIKE SHE WAS
ABOUT ME AND THE SUIT.
AND JUST BECAUSE ARMOR
CAN COVER UP A WOUND
DOESN'T MEAN THAT
IT'S NOT STILL THERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I DID
WHEN SHE TRIED TO HELP ME?
I PUSHED HER AWAY.
BECAUSE I JUST ASSUMED
THAT SHE'D ALWAYS BE THERE.
WELL, I TOOK MY EYES OFF ALICE
TO SPEND THE NIGHT WITH RENEE,
SO IF YOU'RE HAVING
A GUILT PARTY,
MAKE ROOM FOR ONE MORE.
SO THAT'S HOW ALICE GOT OUT?
YOU AND RENEE ARE A THING NOW?
WE'RE NOT A THING.
WE HAD A THING,
WHICH TECHNICALLY
DIDN'T EVEN LAST TILL BREAKFAST,
WHICH SAYS A LOT CONSIDERING
SHE LIVES ABOUT A G.C. JITTERS.
THAT'S IT. COFFEE.
THAT'S HOW WE FIND MARY.
HOW? SHE'S NOT USING
HER CREDIT CARDS.
YEAH, BUT IF THERE'S
ONE THING THAT
A SLEEP-DEPRIVED MARY
HAMILTON CANNOT LIVE WITHOUT,
IT IS COFFEE, AND...
YEAH. SHE USED HER REWARDS CARD
AT A G.C. JITTERS
OUTSIDE OF METROPOLIS
TWO HOURS AGO.
THAT'S OUR MARY. LEAVE
NO REWARD POINT BEHIND.
LOOKS LIKE YOU KNOW HER
BETTER THAN YOU THINK.
OK. SO THE NEAREST
TRACKER TO THAT
G.C. JITTERS LOCATION IS...
BROWNSVILLE PUB?
ENOUGH O NEG FOR A WHOLE HUMAN.
IT IS AMAZING WHAT TWO PEOPLE
WITH NARY A CONSCIENCE
BETWEEN THEM CAN PULL OFF.
I HOPE THIS GOES BETTER
THAN MY LAST TRANSFUSION.
NOCTURNA.
YOU WERE THERE.
RIGHT. YOU MEAN WHEN
YOU SAVED YOUR OWN SKIN
BY SICCING THAT OFF-BRAND
VAMPIRE ONTO MOI
BY LURING HER WITH THE FACT
THAT I HAD DESERT ROSE
IN MY BLOOD,
WHICH WAS ONLY THERE
BECAUSE YOU GAVE MY MOM
THE CHOICE BETWEEN HER OR ME
WITH ONLY ONE CURE BETWEEN US?
YEAH, I REMEMBER.
WE'VE COME A LONG WAY,
HAVEN'T WE?
HMM. YOU KNOW, FOR SO LONG,
ALL I WANTED WAS FOR YOU
TO BE OUT OF MY LIFE.
I SHOULD JUST STICK
AN EMBOLISM IN YOUR IV
AND FINALLY JUST
BE DONE WITH YOU.
AHEM. HEH HEH.
OR, UH, OPTION "B,"
YOU COULD FINISH MY OIL CHANGE,
AND YOU WILL NEVER HAVE TO
SEE ME AGAIN.
ACTUALLY, THAT'S
WHAT I'M AFRAID OF.
HARD TO BELIEVE, RIGHT?
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE ALONE.
I KNOW THE FEELING.
BUT YOU WON'T BE.
I'M GONNA STAY WITH YOU THROUGH
THIS WHOLE MARY METAMORPHOSIS.
YOU'D BE A LOT EASIER TO TRUST
IF YOU WEREN'T A SERIAL KILLER.
A SERIAL KILLER
WHO HASN'T LEFT YOU,
DOUBTED YOU, OR IGNORED YOU.
DO YOU REALLY WANT TO BE
ALONE RIGHT NOW,
OR DO YOU WANT HELP FROM THE
ONLY FAMILY YOU HAVE LEFT?
- MARQUIS?
- HI, MOM!
- WHERE ARE YOU?
- RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
HA! MADE YOU LOOK.
WHY ARE YOU CALLING?
TO TELL YOU TURN ON
THE TV TOMORROW,
9 A.M. SHARP, ANY CHANNEL.
- WHY?
- BECAUSE, MAMA,
I'M GONNA MAKE YOU SO PROUD.
BYE-BYE, LITTLE ROBO NARCS.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO GET
RID OF THESE LATER.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
LIKE MY DONOR SHOULD TAKE
AN UBER HOME.
GIRAFFES OR ELEPHANTS?
ELEPHANTS. THEY HAVE
LONGER MEMORIES.
I KNOW WE WEREN'T
EACH OTHER'S...
FIRST CHOICE
IN THE SISTER DEPARTMENT,
BUT I'M, UM...
I'M REALLY GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
KATE WOULD HAVE NEVER
DONE THIS FOR ME.
HARD SAME.
KATE WOULD HAVE NEVER
LET ME DO ANYTHING.
AT LEAST YOU BELIEVED
I WAS CAPABLE
OF DOING MORE THAN WHAT
EVERYONE ELSE EXPECTS OF ME.
WELL, I'M GLAD THE NEW YOU
FINALLY AGREES
THAT EVERYONE SUCKS.
YOU KNOW, THE FIRST SIGN
OF SPROUTS,
KATE WOULD HAVE LOCKED YOU
AWAY IN ARKHAM.
YEAH. THEN SHE WOULD HAVE FELT
REALLY BAD ABOUT IT IN HER JOURNAL.
HEH!
POLICE! YOU'RE IN POSSESSION
OF A STOLEN VEHICLE!
EXIT WITH YOUR HANDS UP!
UH, THIS WOULD BE A GOOD TIME
TO USE YOUR PHEROMONE POWERS.
I CAN'T DO IT THROUGH THE DOOR.
YOU WANT TO OPEN UP? I DON'T.
STOP!
OH, MY GOD! STOP!
I THINK WE HIT HIM.
I THINK THAT'S
A REASON TO KEEP GOING.
OH, THANK GOD. I THINK WE
MISSED HIM WITH THE WHEELS.
HE PROBABLY HAS A CONCUSSION.
HE NEEDS A RIDE TO THE HOSPITAL.
I'M SURE ONE WILL COME ALONG.
YOU DON'T NEED TO BE
THAT PERSON.
I CAN'T JUST LEAVE HIM!
THE OLD YOU CAN'T LEAVE HIM.
REMEMBER HER?
THE ONE WHO PUTS EVERYONE'S
NEEDS ABOVE HER OWN
AND NEVER GETS
ANYTHING IN RETURN?
THE NEW YOU PUTS
HERSELF FIRST, HMM,
AND LEAVES BEHIND
ANYONE WHO TRIES TO STOP HER.
HOBBIES INCLUDE
LONG WALKS ON THE BEACH
AND NOT BEING INCARCERATED.
SORRY, OLD ME.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
WE NEED TO DITCH THE NANOBOTS.
- PUNCH IT!
- CONSIDER IT PUNCHED!
WHOO-HOO!
HOW FAST DOES THIS THING GO?
WHY'D YOU STOP?
I DIDN'T.
SO CLOSE.
MARY, YOU'RE GONNA BE FINE.
- WE HAVE A CURE.
- A CURE? HOW?
IT'S A LONG STORY, BUT
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
IT'S PROBABLY THE LAST NIGHT
YOU'RE YOU, BUT LOOK.
THIS WILL STOP THE INFECTION.
YOU COULD BE YOU AGAIN.
THE OLD YOU,
THE ONE THEY CAN USE,
THE ONE THEY CAN IGNORE
UNTIL THEY NEED TO TROT HER OUT
FOR BATTEAM ASSEMBLE.
YOU KNOW HOW WE FOUND YOU?
LUKE KNEW YOU COULDN'T
RESIST COLLECTING
YOUR DAMN G.C. JITTERS POINTS.
THAT'S WHAT BEST FRIENDS
KNOW ABOUT EACH OTHER, MARY.
LOOK AT ME!
YOU WERE THE FIRST PERSON
TO BELIEVE IN ME.
NOW I NEED YOU TO DO IT AGAIN.
THERE THEY GO, TELLING
YOU HOW TO THINK.
I DON'T WANT TO END UP
IN ARKHAM.
IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE THAT WAY.
PROMISE?
WHAT WILL YOU DO TO ME
IF I DON'T TAKE THE CURE?
I WOULD HAVE TO KEEP YOU CONFINED
UNTIL WE FIGURE SOMETHING OUT.
WE CAN'T JUST LET YOU
HURT PEOPLE.
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
WHAT DID YOU DO TO ME?
MARY, I AM TRYING TO SAVE YOU.
WELL, MAYBE I DON'T
WANT TO BE SAVED.
THIS ISN'T YOU TALKING.
NO. THIS IS YOU NOT LISTENING.
IF YOU THINK THAT
I'M NOT MYSELF,
THEN YOU DON'T KNOW ME AT ALL.
HA HA HA!
IT'S TIME I STEP
OUT OF YOUR SHADOW
AND INTO MY OWN SUNLIGHT.
UNH!
WHERE'S MARY?
SHE'S NOT MARY ANYMORE.
SHE DIDN'T WANT TO BE SAVED.
BUT WE'RE NOT GIVING UP ON HER.
YOU DON'T GET IT.
I THINK SHE'S GIVEN UP ON US.
ALL OF GOTHAM IS ROCKED
BY THIS STUNNING
NEW DEVELOPMENT.
THE SURPRISE RESIGNATION
OF CEO RYAN WILDER
HAS LEFT WAYNE ENTERPRISES
VULNERABLE
TO A HOSTILE TAKEOVER.
WHAT THIS MEANS
FOR THIS LEGENDARY PILLAR
OF GOTHAM CITY IS STILL
A MYSTERY,
BUT WE ARE STANDING BY HERE
AT WAYNE TOWER,
WHERE WE ARE TOLD
THE NEW CEO OF WAYNE ENTERPRISES
WILL BE MAKING
A STATEMENT SHORTLY.
NOW YOU KNOW WHY THE
BATMOBILE'S PARKED AT A METER.
NEWS VANS COMPLETELY
BLOCKING THE GARAGE.
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
ABLE TO GET IN ANYWAY.
OUR SECURITY CLEARANCES
HAVE BEEN REVOKED.
WE ARE OFFICIALLY SHUT OUT
OF WAYNE TOWER.
WHAT ABOUT THE BATCAVE?
I BARELY HAD ENOUGH TIME
TO INITIATE THE LOCKDOWN,
BUT, YEAH,
THE BATCAVE IS SEALED.
WE'RE NOT GETTING BACK IN THERE,
BUT WE HAVE THE BATSUIT,
THE BATMOBILE,
AND NOT MUCH ELSE.
I AM SO SORRY, LUKE.
I TRADED AWAY THE WAYNE
LEGACY FOR NOTHING.
YOU DID IT FOR MARY.
THAT'S NOT NOTHING.
GOOD MORNING,
CITIZENS OF GOTHAM!
I AM HONORED AND PROUD
TO INTRODUCE MYSELF
AS THE NEW LEADER IN BUSINESS.
YOU SEE, AS TIMES ARE CHANGING,
IT IS TIME THAT WE SEE
THE BIG MONEYMAKERS FOLLOW SUIT.
NOW I NOW THIS TOWN
SEES ME AS A BIT
OF A SERIAL ENTREPRENEUR,
BUT AS THE NEW CEO
OF WAYNE ENTERPRISES,
I PROMISE YOU A FRONT ROW SEAT
TO THE BLEEDING EDGE
OF THE INDUSTRY,
WHERE YOU'LL NOT ONLY SEE
INSPIRING INNOVATION
FROM VISIONARY THOUGHT LEADERS,
BUT YOU'LL SEE THAT WE'RE GONNA
HAVE A WHOLE LOT MORE FUN.
WHILE I WAS HIRED
TO FILL THE COFFERS
OF MY SHAREHOLDERS,
MY MAIN MISSION IS TO PUT
A SMILE ON EVERYONE'S FACE.
AS MANY OF YOU KNOW, I WORKED
ALONGSIDE MY MOTHER JADA JET...
MMM. I AM SO HUNGOVER.
THEN AGAIN, I WAS
PRACTICALLY TURNING
INTO THE HUMAN VERSION OF A
LONG ISLAND ICED TEA LAST NIGHT.
I NEED HASH BROWNS
AND COFFEE STAT.
WHAT COULD POSSIBLY BE
TAKING YOU SO LONG?
YOU KNOW, AS MUCH AS I
MAKE IT LOOK EFFORTLESS,
IT TAKES TIME TO MAKE
BAD LOOK THIS GOOD.
♪ BREAK AN ILLUSION
MY... HOW YOU HAVE BLOSSOMED.
♪ AND IT FEELS
I THINK YOUR DIABOLICAL DEBUT
DESERVES MORE THAN
A ROADSIDE GREASY SPOON.
I DON'T CARE WHAT WE DO
OR WHERE WE GO
AS LONG AS IT'S FUN.
AND NOW I CALL YOU TO JOIN ME
AT THE PEAK OF GREATNESS.
HMM. WELL, HE CERTAINLY
LOOKS LIKE FUN.
♪ BEING BAD, YEAH
GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD!