OK. GET ON HER,
GET ON HER.
GO, GO, GO, GO!
OK, OK.
SHAKES HER DEFENDER.
PULLS UP FROM WAY DOWNTOWN,
FIRES, AAAAND...
MISSES. AW. BRICK CITY, BABY.
SHUT UP.
YO! COME ON. LET'S GO!
HANG ON A SECOND.
WHAT THE?
OH, HELL, NO!
HELP... HELP ME.
RAAGGGH!
AAH!
OH, MY GOD.
YOU'RE STANDING
ON THE FREAKING EVIDENCE.
MA'AM, THIS AREA'S OFF LIMITS.
I'M GONNA PRETEND YOU DIDN'T
JUST CALL ME MA'AM
AND INSTEAD ASK YOU TO LEAVE.
THIS CASE BELONGS
TO CITY HALL NOW.
PACK IT UP, BOYS.
FREAK PATROL'S ON THE SCENE.
YOUR AMBIGUOUS
YET FAR-REACHING POWER
SUPERSEDES OURS.
MISS YOU, TOO, DETECTIVE.
- ALL RIGHT. LET'S GO.
- TAKE HIM TO THE CLINIC
ON BENNETT,
ASK FOR MARY HAMILTON.
WHO IS IT NOW, MONTOYA...
POLLEN BOY, CANDYMAN?
TELL THE COMMISSIONER
TO PREP FOR ALL HANDS ON DECK.
THINGS ARE ABOUT TO GET
UGLY AROUND HERE.
THE VICTIM IS CHRIS HAYNER,
TRICORNER RESIDENT FOUND
ENCASED IN A BEEHIVE
IN ROBISON PARK.
YOU THINK SOMEONE
WENT THROUGH THE TROUBLE
OF FILLING A SHED WITH FLOWERS
TO DRAW IN BEES TO, WHAT,
STING THIS GUY TO DEATH?
I THINK THE PERP
LITERALLY BLOOMED
THE FLOWERS THEMSELVES,
WEAPONIZING
THE NATURAL WORLD AROUND THEM.
WHAT AM I MISSING?
POISON IVY.
MORE SPECIFICALLY, HER NEW HOST.
ALICE TURNED OVER IVY'S
VINE TO ME YESTERDAY.
IT WAS DEAD, MEANING
IT HAD ALREADY INFECTED SOMEONE.
I THINK WHOEVER DID THIS
IS THAT SOMEONE.
HOW DID YOU GET
POISON IVY'S VINE?
WHILE YOU WERE SLURPING CAVIAR
OFF OF MUMMY'S FINE CHINA,
SOME OF US WERE IN THE
FIELD PROTECTING THIS CITY.
MM-HMM. YOU JUST
SO HAPPENED TO STUMBLE
ACROSS A BATMAN TROPHY WHILE YOU WERE
TAKING A STROLL THROUGH THE PARK?
THE CHERRY BLOSSOMS ARE SO
GORGEOUS THIS TIME OF YEAR.
TRUST ME. I ALREADY
TRIED TO GET IT OUT OF HER.
WHY AREN'T YOU TELLING ME
WHAT YOU'RE NOT TELLING ME?
YOU LOST ME ON
THE DOUBLE NEGATIVE.
GUYS, WE DON'T HAVE
TIME FOR THIS.
TRUST ME. I TRIED.
FOUND THE VIC'S PHONE
AT THE SCENE.
IT'S PASSCODE-PROTECTED,
BUT I THINK
THERE'S A GOOD CHANCE
HE HAD CONTACT
WITH WHOEVER DID THIS TO HIM.
MY COMPUTER CAN CRACK
HIS PASSCODE.
GOOD. I TOLD MARY HAMILTON
TO GIVE ME A CALL
AS SOON AS OUR VIC WAKES UP.
UH, YOU SENT HIM
TO MARY HAMILTON?
SHE'S BEEN OVERSEEING
ALL THE RIVER ROGUE CASES.
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
NO. NO PROBLEM AT ALL.
IN FACT, MARY HAMILTON
IS THE PERFECT PERSON
TO HELP US WITH THIS CASE.
AMEM. I'M GONNA GO CHECK
ON THE VIC'S PROGRESS.
BECAUSE YOU CARE ABOUT A
STRANGER'S LIFE ALL OF A SUDDEN?
YOU'RE RIGHT. I DON'T.
LET'S YOU AND I GO SIT
IN THE BATCAVE TOGETHER
AND WATCH THE COMPUTER
TEDIOUSLY CYCLE
THROUGH ALL THE
ANTI-ENCRYPTION CIPHERS.
HAVE FUN WITH MARY.
WILL DO.
SOPHIE, MAKE YOURSELF AT HOME.
SORRY. HOPE YOU DON'T MIND.
ALICE SPILLED CHERRY
SODA ALL OVER MY LAPTOP.
BESIDES, YOU HAVE MORE EYES
IN THIS CITY THAN I DO.
BLACK GLOVE'S MERCENARIES
STAY INVISIBLE
BY DOING THINGS
THE OLD-FASHIONED WAY.
THEY'RE OFF THE GRID,
THEY'RE OFF THE CLOUD.
SURPRISED THEY USE
ELECTRICITY AT ALL.
FOUND THIS SURVEILLANCE
OF JORDAN'S ATTACKER
LEAVING HER APARTMENT,
BUT I LOST HIM A BLOCK LATER.
SO YOU'RE WAITING FOR HIM
TO SHOW UP ON CAMERAS AGAIN?
UNLESS YOUR MOM
MIRACULOUSLY CAME CLEAN
AND OFFERED UP HER ROLODEX.
I FIGURED WHEN YOU
DIDN'T CALL LAST NIGHT,
CONFRONTING HER ABOUT WHAT
THESE GUYS DID TO MY SISTER
WAS A DEAD END, SO IT'S JUST YOU
AND ME
AND CRISPY JOE'S WONTONS.
MY MOM WASN'T RESPONSIBLE
FOR WHAT HAPPENED TO JORDAN.
HEH HEH. AND YOU BELIEVE HER?
YOU BELIEVE HER.
AND NOW I NEED YOU
TO BELIEVE ME.
MY MOM ISN'T THE MONSTER
YOU THINK SHE IS.
I THINK YOU SHOULD DROP IT.
RYAN, MY SISTER HAD EVIDENCE.
I MEAN, A DRAWING OF
VICTOR FRIES' CRYO CHAMBER
WAS FAXED DIRECTLY
TO YOUR MOM'S OFFICE.
I AM NOT SAYING SHE DIDN'T
INITIATE THE PROJECT.
SO YOU'RE SAYING
SHE IS INVOLVED?
I AM SAYING THAT JADA
PROMISED ME SHE HAD NO IDEA
PEOPLE WERE GOING TO GET HURT.
AND THAT'S GOOD ENOUGH?
3 OF JORDAN'S FRIENDS
DIED BECAUSE
OF YOUR MOM'S INVOLVEMENT
WITH THE FREEZE SERUM.
JORDAN IS STILL IN RECOVERY.
WHAT HAPPENED WAS HORRIBLE.
I AM NOT SAYING IT'S OK.
THEN WHY AREN'T YOU
WONDERING WHY,
AND WHY DOES SHE WANT IT,
AND WHY AREN'T YOU STOPPING HER?
BECAUSE IT'S COMPLICATED.
I PROMISE YOU I WILL TELL
YOU EVERYTHING WHEN I CAN.
WHEN YOU CAN?
RYAN, IT'S ME.
WHAT DOES SHE HAVE OVER YOU?
LET ME HELP.
I CAN GET YOU OUT OF IT.
SHE DOESN'T HAVE
ANYTHING OVER ME.
THEN WHY ARE YOU PROTECTING HER?
SOPHIE, I JUST NEED
YOU TO TRUST ME ON THIS.
- BECAUSE SHE'S YOUR MOM?
- IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE.
OH, REALLY? BECAUSE YOU'RE MAKING
IT SOUND PRETTY FREAKING SIMPLE.
MMM. TELL ME THERE'S
A JAR OF THIS SOMEWHERE.
WHY DID BATWOMAN SEND
YOU HERE TO TORTURE ME?
OH, SHE DIDN'T. I VOLUNTEERED.
OF COURSE YOU DID.
APPARENTLY, THIS IS THE WORK
OF A POISON IVY WANNABE.
THE QUESTION IS
WHAT KIND OF MONSTER
WOULD ENTOMB A MAN
IN A SWARM OF RAVENOUS BEES?
YOU KNOW IT'S BAD
IF IT MAKES ME CRINGE.
OH. I HAVE AN IDEA.
WHY DON'T YOU LEAVE
AND GO FIND OUT?
THAT'S THE THING, STEPPY.
I THINK I ALREADY KNOW WHO
THIS DISTURBED CREATURE IS.
YOU.
I SEE. YOU'RE HAVING
DELUSIONS AGAIN,
AND INSTEAD OF ADMITTING IT
LIKE A NORMAL PERSON,
YOU'RE GASLIGHTING ME
TO AVOID BEING VULNERABLE
WHEN I TELL YOU
I STOPPED CARING.
SWEET, NAIVE MARY.
TSK, TSK, TSK.
LOOK AROUND. YOU'VE TURNED
YOUR CLINIC INTO JUMANJI,
YOU'RE DOWNING WATER
LIKE YOU JUST RAN
THE GOTHAM CITY MARATHON,
AND IF YOU THINK THAT
THAT IS ANYTHING
OTHER THAN A POISON IVY RASH,
YOU SHOULD GIVE BACK
THAT SHINY MEDICAL DEGREE.
SERIOUSLY? LOOK AT ME.
I'M DR. MARY HAMILTON.
DO YOU ACTUALLY THINK
I'M CAPABLE
OF HURTING ANYONE,
MUCH LESS DOING THIS?
CHRIS?
- AAH! AAH!
- CHRIS?
IT'S OK. YOU'RE SAFE NOW.
- HELP ME!
- HEY. RELAX.
PLEASE, PLEASE GET AWAY FROM ME.
CHRIS, I'M YOUR DOCTOR.
YOU'RE SAFE NOW.
I'M TAKING CARE OF YOU.
TAKING CARE OF ME?
YOU DID THIS TO ME!
OHH. AS I WAS SAYING.
OK. TEAM MEETING
IN THE LITERAL
DEAD OF THE NIGHT.
SO WHY ARE WE HERE?
SO YOU KNOW HOW WE HAVE
THE BATTEAM RULES
AND THE FIRST RULE IS
HOLDING EACH OTHER ACCOUNTABLE?
YEAH.
SO...
SO?
I'M...
YOU'RE...
OH, WOW!
I THOUGHT WATCHING
KATE COME OUT WAS TORTURE.
WAIT. YOU'RE COMING OUT?
WHAT? NO. OH. IN A WAY.
I... I'M NOT COMING OUT
BECAUSE I'M NOT GAY,
BUT THAT'S BESIDE THE POINT.
MARY, MY GOD.
I'M POISON IVY.
AND I... KNOW WHAT YOU ALL
MUST BE THINKING.
"MARY, THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE
BECAUSE YOU'RE SO NORMAL
"AND COMPASSIONATE,
SO HOW COULD YOU BECOME
SOME PLANT WHISPERING
ATTEMPTED MURDERER?"
AND THEN I REALIZE
I CAN'T EVEN REMEMBER
WHERE I... WAS EARLIER TODAY.
IT'S BECAUSE I WAS
IN SOME FUGUE STATE
TORTURING CHRIS HAYNER,
WHO I DON'T EVEN KNOW.
I'M... I'M SORRY. WHAT?!
SEE, THE LITTLE WORKER BEE
IN THE HIVE, WHEN HE
CRACKED HIS EYES OPEN,
HE BLAMED QUEEN MARY FOR
TURNING HIM INTO AN EPIPEN AD.
THEN HE'S SEEING THINGS.
I MEAN, HIS EYES ARE
PRACTICALLY SWOLLEN SHUT.
I MEAN, HE JUST
EXPERIENCED A MAJOR TRAUMA.
OK. THEN EXPLAIN MY SUDDEN
OBSESSION WITH PLANTS.
YOU'RE A DOCTOR.
YOU CARE FOR THINGS.
OR MY SUDDEN CONSTANT,
UNQUENCHABLE THIRST.
YOU'RE DEHYDRATED.
MARY, YOU WORK
IN THE CLINIC ALL DAY AND NIGHT.
YOU DON'T EAT OR SLEEP.
YOU'RE ALWAYS PUTTING
EVERYONE'S NEEDS
BEFORE YOUR OWN.
UH, GUYS, WHY WERE
CHRIS HAYNER'S
LAST 3 TEXTS TO MARY
THIS MORNING?
AND WE'RE ALL ON THE SAME PAGE.
WELL, THAT WAS
AN EXCRUCIATING PROCESS.
YOU KNEW MARY WAS
INFECTED BY THE VINE.
THAT'S WHY YOU WERE BEING
SO COY IN MONTOYA'S OFFICE.
I JUST FIGURED
THE LAST THING ANYONE NEEDED
WAS FOR MARY TO END UP
ON RENEE'S WALL OF WEIRD.
OH. MUTING THE BOSS.
I'M SURE THAT'S GONNA
END REALLY WELL.
MONTOYA DOESN'T NEED TO
KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT THIS.
OK. I SEE. IT'S FINE
WHEN WE THROW ALICE IN ARKHAM,
BUT, OH, POOR, SWEET,
INNOCENT MARY,
YEAH, WE SHOULD
PROTECT HER AT ALL COSTS.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- WHAT ONE DOES
WHEN THEY REALIZE
THEY CAN CONTROL
MOTHER FREAKING EARTH.
I NEARLY KILLED SOMEONE,
AND I DON'T KNOW WHY
OR WHEN THIS INFECTION IS
GONNA MAKE ME TRANSFORM AGAIN,
AND UNTIL WE FIGURE IT OUT,
I AM A THREAT TO EVERYONE...
NOT ME.
SO I'M STAYING RIGHT HERE.
WELL, YOU CAN TAKE
THE GIRL OUT OF THE GCPD.
LOOKS LIKE YOU GOT
THE SAME PARTNER.
SOPHIE MOORE.
ONLY A FELLOW WORKAHOLIC
WOULD ASSUME
I'D BE AT THE OFFICE AT 2 A.M.
THIS IS AN OFFICE?
WOULDN'T HAVE GUESSED.
I MEAN, I THOUGHT
DETECTIVE MONTOYA
WAS ON TRACK TO BE
THE NEXT COMMISSIONER.
NOW YOU'RE SHARING A BASEMENT
WITH A LEAKY PIPE. OUCH.
AT LEAST I HAVE A JOB.
I QUIT THE CROWS BY CHOICE.
RIGHT BEFORE KANE'S
OWN AGENTS TRIED TO KILL HIM?
REAL PROFILE IN COURAGE.
I'M HERE TO LET
YOU RETURN A FAVOR.
EXCUSE ME. THEN PLEASE GO ON.
I'D LOVE TO HEAR
WHAT YOU'VE DONE FOR ME
OTHER THAN FLASH
YOUR CROWS BADGE
TO STEAL MY BEST CASES.
IF I WEREN'T WILLING
TO BABYSIT ALICE,
YOU'D NEVER BE ABLE
TO PROVE TO THE MAYOR
THAT YOU'RE CAPABLE OF COLLECTING
ALL THESE BATMAN WEAPONS,
AND WE BOTH KNOW WITHOUT ALICE
NONE OF THESE CASES
ARE GETTING SOLVED.
FINE. I'LL BITE. WHAT?
SOMEONE EXPERIMENTED
ON MY SISTER
WITH A VARIANT OF VICTOR
FRIES' FREEZE SERUM.
I NEED ALL THE DATA YOUR
TASKFORCE COLLECTED ON FRIES
AND THAT SERUM.
WE DON'T HAVE HALF
OF WHAT BATWOMAN DOES.
AREN'T YOU PALS?
GO SHINE A FLASHLIGHT
IN THE AIR.
I WOULD EXCEPT WE'RE NOT SEEING
EYE TO EYE ON THIS.
DRAMA.
YOU WANT ME TO GET TWO STRAWS?
WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT
THE BLACK GLOVE SOCIETY,
SPECIFICALLY HIM?
THIS GUY LED THE EXPERIMENTS.
IS YOUR SISTER OK?
DO YOU ACTUALLY CARE?
IF YOUR SISTER SURVIVED
WHAT THEY DID TO HER,
THEN I'D COUNT MY LUCKY STARS,
AND THEN I'D FORGET
I EVER HEARD OF BLACK GLOVE.
- WELL, WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
- ABSOLUTELY NOTHING
EXCEPT THAT EVERYONE
WHO KNOWS ANYTHING
ABOUT BLACK GLOVE
USUALLY ENDS UP DEAD.
CAREFUL, MOORE.
THERE ARE WORSE THINGS
THAN ENDING UP LIKE ME.
DO YOU REMEMBER
MEETING HIM ON TWINGE?
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
I WAS ON TWINGE.
I'VE NEVER SEEN THIS
GUY BEFORE IN MY LIFE.
ARE YOUR EYES GREEN
IN YOUR PROFILE PICTURE?
NO. I THINK IT'S
JUST BAD LIGHTING.
MAYBE HE WAS STALKING ME,
OR MAYBE HE WAS SOME
DATE RAPE GUY
AND I FOUND OUT ABOUT IT.
UH, SEEMS LIKE HE JUST
WASN'T THAT INTO YOU.
YEAH. ACCORDING TO YOUR DMs,
WHICH I MERELY SKIMMED
FOR KEY WORDS,
HE SAID YOU SEEMED "SWEET."
OHH! OH.
SO YOU SUFFOCATED HIM IN HONEY.
CLEVER GIRL. HEH.
I THINK I WANT TO
DATE POISON IVY MARY.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
HOLD ON. REJECTION?
I ALMOST TOOK
AN INNOCENT MAN'S LIFE.
OK. MARY'S RIGHT. THAT'S
A PRETTY SCREWED UP REASON
TO NEARLY DROWN A GUY.
I DON'T KNOW. IS IT, THOUGH?
I MEAN, I'VE NEVER BEEN
ACCUSED OF BEING, UM, SWEET,
BUT, UH, IT'S BASICALLY
LIKE SAYING,
YOU KNOW, "YOU'RE PLEASANT
BUT INSTANTLY FORGETTABLE."
IT'S LIKE THE BEIGE
OF COMPLIMENTS,
- THE SWIPE LEFT OF NICE...
- WE GET IT.
YOU DON'T REALLY THINK THAT'S
HOW PEOPLE SEE YOU, RIGHT?
HEY. DO YOU REMEMBER GOING TO
A HARDWARE STORE THIS MORNING?
SHOULD I?
WELL, YOU BOUGHT
A FLOWERING POT,
FERTILIZER, AND A WATERING CAN,
AND ACCORDING TO YOUR
PHONE'S GEO DATA,
ONCE YOU LEFT THE STORE,
YOU WENT TO A VACANT LOT
IN BURNSIDE.
PLEASE DON'T TELL ME
I HURT ANYONE ELSE.
WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY
ANYTHING ABOUT MARY?
I WAS WONDERING HOW THIS
WOULD END UP MY FAULT.
YOU OBVIOUSLY KNEW
SOMETHING WAS UP.
HOW'D YOU FIGURE IT OUT?
UH, THE QUESTION ISN'T
HOW I FIGURED IT OUT.
IT'S HOW THE HELL YOU DIDN'T.
YOU'RE HER ROOMMATE,
YOU HAVE A BILLION DOLLARS
OF BATTECH AT YOUR DISPOSAL,
AND YOUR NUMBER TWO IS
A CERTIFIABLE GENIUS.
ONE OF YOU SHOULD HAVE NOTICED.
THE FERTILIZER BAG IS EMPTY,
BUT THE GROUND'S NOT DISTURBED.
NOTHING WAS PLANTED.
WHY WAS MARY HERE?
MARY HAMILTON, YOU DIRTY GIRL.
HE'S STILL ALIVE.
OH. WELL, IT'S ONLY
HER FIRST DAY.
I WONDER WHAT THIS GUY
DID TO MARY.
I DON'T KNOW, BUT HE TRIED
TO KILL SOPHIE AND ME
AND FREEZE SOPHIE'S SISTER.
SOMEHOW, MARY
MANAGED TO TURN ONE
OF BLACK GLOVE'S MOST
DANGEROUS OPERATIVES
INTO A, UH, GARDEN TURNIP.
I'M NOT SURE IF THAT'S
IMPRESSIVE OR JUST
REALLY, REALLY BAD.
I DON'T SUPPOSE
YOU HAVE A BATSHOVEL
IN THAT BELT.
RIGHT.
OH. SORRY. HOW DID I TRACK DOWN
AN ELUSIVE BLACK OPS
ORGANIZATION?
UH, YOU TRACKED THE P.O. BOX
VIRGIL GETTY WAS USING
THROUGH THE COMPANY
THAT SOLD HIM
THE CRYOGENIC MEDICAL SUPPLIES
THAT HE USED
ON THE FREEZE SERUM VICTIMS.
SOPHIE'S BEEN A
BLOODHOUND WITH THIS GUY.
I'M SURE SHE TRIED THAT.
YEAH. WELL, SOPHIE DOESN'T
HAVE AN MD AFTER HER NAME.
IT LOOKS LIKE DR. HAMILTON
USED HER TITLE
TO BYPASS PRIVACY LAWS.
VIOLATION OF MEDICAL ETHICS.
HARLEY QUINN, HERE YOU COME.
PERHAPS SOMEONE SHOULD
TELL SOPHIE
THAT THE GUY WHO TRIED
TO BURN US ALIVE
AND FREEZE HER SISTER
TO DEATH IS HANGING
FROM A SEWER PIPE UNDER WAYNE.
NO. WE HAVE ENOUGH PROBLEMS
WITHOUT SOPHIE FINDING MORE.
WELL, "MOORE" IS
LITERALLY HER NAME,
AND AS A VICTIM
OF SOPHIE'S BACKHAND,
I'D SAY SHE CAN HANDLE HERSELF.
I SAID SHE STAYS OUT OF IT!
OK. CAN WE GET BACK TO ME
FREAKING OUT OVER THE FACT
THAT I'M TURNING
INTO AN UBERVILLAIN
AGAINST MY WILL?
WHY IS THIS HAPPENING?
POISON IVY'S AN ECOTERRORIST.
NEITHER OF YOUR VICTIMS
HAD ANY PUBLIC RECORD
OF ACTIVELY HURTING
THE ENVIRONMENT.
YEAH, BUT THE BATVILLAIN WEAPONS
DON'T NECESSARILY MEAN
THE SAME M.O.
LIAM CRANDLE DIDN'T
HAVE THE SAME AGENDA
AS THE OG MAD HATTER.
THAT'S A GOOD POINT.
UM, CHRIS CALLED YOU SWEET,
YOU DIPPED HIM IN HONEY.
VIRGIL FROZE JORDAN,
SO YOU USED MOTHER NATURE
TO IMMOBILIZE HIM.
SO... MAYBE
THE CHEMICAL PHEROMONES
FROM THE POISON IVY
ALLOW ME TO COMMUNICATE
WITH NATURE WHILE
HEIGHTENING THE THINGS
THAT I'M PASSIONATE ABOUT
LIKE JUSTICE?
WELL, SEEING AS THAT M.O. TRACKS
AND, UH... AHEM...
I KILLED YOUR MOTHER,
I'M REALLY NOT LOOKING
FORWARD TO BEING TURNED
INTO A CABBAGE,
SO WE SHOULD FIND OUT
EXACTLY WHAT TURNS DR. JEKYLL
INTO MRS. HIDE MY
VICTIMS UNDER A POT.
DAMN IT.
WHAT DOES SHE WANT?
YOU, MY DEAR,
DEAD OR ALIVE.
MAKING HOUSE CALLS NOW?
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME YOU FOUND
ANOTHER POISON IVY VIC?
IT'S 5:00 IN THE MORNING.
I FIGURED YOU WERE ASLEEP.
I DON'T SLEEP, RYAN,
ESPECIALLY WHEN SOMEONE'S
OUT THERE WITH PAM'S ABILITIES.
- WHERE'S THE VIC?
- IN MY CUSTODY.
YEAH. WELL, I NEED TO
TALK TO HIM.
I NEED TO KNOW WHAT HE SAW,
WHAT HE KNOWS.
HE'S UNCONSCIOUS AT THE MOMENT.
WHEN HE'S TALKING,
I WILL CALL YOU.
OH. JUST LIKE CHRIS HAYNER?
IS THAT A COINCIDENCE
OR CONVENIENCE?
YOU WANTED TO PARTNER
WITH BATWOMAN, RIGHT?
THEN YOU NEED TO
TRUST MY PROCESS.
RYAN IS FLAILING.
WHAT DID YOU MEAN RENEE
WANTED ME DEAD OR ALIVE?
OH. RENEE AND POISON PAM
HAVE A BACKSTORY.
WHAT KIND OF BACKSTORY?
OH. I DON'T WANT TO BE A GOSSIP.
SPILL.
IF YOU INSIST.
SO... THEY MET,
FELL MADLY IN LOVE,
KISSY, KISSY, KISSY.
THEN PAM FELL VICTIM TO SOME
EVIL SCIENTIST'S EXPERIMENT.
OBVIOUSLY PAM'S METAMORPHOSIS
INTO "LITTLE SHOP OF HORRORS"
GOT IN THE WAY OF SEXY TIME,
WHICH WAS A BIG PROBLEM
FOR RENEE
AS SHE WAS A GCPD DETECTIVE.
CRISIS OF THE HEART,
BORING, BORING, BORING.
ULTIMATELY, RENEE CALLED BATMAN,
WHO CONVINCED HER TO LURE
THE LOVE OF HER LIFE
INTO HIS TRAP.
WHY WOULD SOMEONE
INFECTED WITH POISON IVY
TARGET A BLACK GLOVE OPERATIVE?
IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE
UNLESS HE HAD
A PERSONAL CONNECTION TO THEM.
IF I KNEW, I WOULD TELL YOU.
WOULD YOU?
BECAUSE I'M BEGINNING
TO FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE HIDING THINGS
FROM ME, RYAN.
WHERE'S THE VIC?
THAT'S REALLY INTENSE.
SO RENEE SOLD OUT THE LOVE
OF HER LIFE TO BATMAN?
AND HE BURIED HER
DEEP UNDERGROUND
AWAY FROM WATER AND SUNLIGHT
TO SHRIVEL UP AND NOT DIE.
CAN YOU IMAGINE GOING
WITHOUT SKIN CREAM
FOR ALL THOSE YEARS?
IMAGINE WHAT SHE'D DO TO SOMEONE
SHE BARELY EVEN KNOWS.
OK. I THINK MARY'S HEARD ENOUGH.
WHAT? I'M NOT TRYING
TO SCARE HER.
IT'S JUST LIAM
ENDED UP IN ARKHAM,
KILLER CROC IN A CAGE,
AND NORA FRIES
WOULD RATHER FACE DEATH
OVER BEING HELD CAPTIVE AGAIN.
I JUST THINK WE ARE
DOING OURSELVES A DISSERVICE
TO DENY THE PREDICTABLE OUTCOME
OF ANYONE WHO COMES IN CONTACT
WITH BATMAN'S TROPHIES.
AS A GIRL WHO SPENT OVER A
DECADE OF HER LIFE LOCKED
IN A SMALL ROOM,
I JUST WANT YOU TO AVOID
ENDING UP THE WAY THEY DID.
WATCHING THE WOMAN I LOVED GO
FROM THIS COMPASSIONATE,
SELFLESS PERSON
TO THIS THING THAT COULD
JUSTIFY KILLING
DOZENS OF PEOPLE,
IT BROKE ME, RYAN,
AND NOW SHE'S INFECTED
SOMEONE ELSE,
SO TO PRETEND LIKE
I DON'T KNOW HOW THIS ENDS
AND NOT DO EVERYTHING
IN MY POWER TO STOP IT,
IT WOULDN'T BE FAIR TO ME,
TO THE CITY,
OR TO THE PAM I USED TO KNOW.
SO CALL ME
WHEN YOUR GUY WAKES UP.
WE NEED TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT MY TRIGGER IS.
MAYBE IT'S A WORD
OR A SERIES OF WORDS.
ACTUALLY, I'M STARTING
TO FEEL A LITTLE FUNNY.
OK. FUNNY HOW?
MY VISION'S A LITTLE BLURRY.
OK. MAYBE YOU'RE DEHYDRATED.
RENEE'S ON MY ASS.
WE DON'T HAVE A LOT OF TIME
TO FIGURE THIS OUT.
WE COULD ASK SOPHIE
TO ASK VIRGIL
IF HE SAID OR DID ANYTHING
THAT TRIGGERED MARY.
SOPHIE'S NOT WITH VIRGIL.
OH. HEH HEH. OOPS.
WHAT DID YOU DO?
SO... SOPHIE HAS BEEN
A GREAT ROOMMATE.
YOU KNOW, SHE PUTS
MY DISHES AWAY,
SHE CLEANS MY CLOTHES
WITH THAT FABRIC SOFTENER
THAT DOESN'T IRRITATE
MY SENSITIVE SKIN.
ALICE, WHAT DID YOU DO?
SOPHIE REALLY WANTED TO
INTERROGATE VIRGIL,
AND I DIDN'T WANT TO
KEEP SECRETS FROM MY ROOMIE.
YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'VE JUST DONE.
SO SUE ME FOR HAVING
GUILT FOR ONCE IN MY LIFE.
SERIOUSLY, JUST STOP TALKING.
I DON'T GET IT.
WHY CAN'T SOPHIE KNOW
WHERE VIRGIL IS?
I'LL BE BACK.
CALL ME IF ANYTHING
CHANGES HERE.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
TO STOP SOPHIE FROM MAKING
A HUGE MISTAKE.
HELLO AGAIN.
I KNOW. YOU THOUGHT
YOU BURNED ME ALIVE,
BUT NOPE, I LIVED
TO DO THE SAME TO YOU.
I'VE GOT SOME QUESTIONS
ABOUT YOUR EMPLOYER.
WHO HIRED YOU TO TAKE MY SISTER?
LET ME REPHRASE THAT.
WAS IT JADA JET?
TECHNICALLY, I WAS HIRED
BY MARLA ELLIOT DECADES AGO.
ELLIOT. AS IN TOMMY ELLIOT?
HIS MOTHER. THOUGHT TOMMY
HAD BEHAVIORAL PROBLEMS.
WELL, SHE GOT THAT RIGHT
SINCE HE TURNED
INTO THAT PSYCHO HUSH.
BEFORE THAT, SHE FORMED
A GROUP OF OTHER PARENTS
WITH BAD SEED KIDS,
SWAPPED HORROR STORIES,
DISCUSSED TREATMENTS,
MEDS, WHATEVER.
LIKE SECRET GROUP THERAPY
FOR RICH PEOPLE
TO TALK ABOUT THEIR
SCREWED UP KIDS.
I DON'T KNOW OF ANY SELF-HELP
GROUPS THAT EMPLOY A MILITIA.
THEY'RE CALLED BLACK GLOVE
BECAUSE THEY DON'T LEAVE A TRACE.
TITANS OF INDUSTRY
SPENDING MILLIONS ON R&D
TO FIX THEIR KIDS' BRAINS...
NOT GREAT FOR PUBLIC IMAGE.
YEAH. NEITHER IS INJECTING
TWENTYSOMETHINGS
WITH FATAL FREEZE SERUM.
MY CLIENTS WOULD AGREE WITH YOU,
WHICH IS EXACTLY WHY WE
CLEAN UP AFTER OURSELVES.
MY SISTER NEARLY DIED!
3 OF HER FRIENDS DID!
WHY? WHAT DOES JADA WANT?
- FINE.
- ENOUGH!
SERIOUSLY?
I HAVE TO FIND OUT FROM ALICE
THAT YOU FOUND THIS GUY?
I SAID I WOULD TELL
YOU EVERYTHING!
- WHEN?
- WHEN IT'S SAFE.
SAFE FROM WHAT?
SAFE FROM WHAT, RYAN?
FROM HER? FROM JADA? WHO?
I'M SORRY.
YOU WANT MY TRUST?
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO EARN IT
BECAUSE RIGHT NOW IT LOOKS LIKE
YOU'RE TAKING
THE SIDE OF A WOMAN
WHO SANCTIONED MURDER OVER ME,
YOUR ACTUAL FRIEND!
NO, NO!
HE'S DEAD.
GUESS YOU GET TO KEEP MOMMY'S
SECRET A LITTLE LONGER.
WHEN BRUCE MET PAM ISLEY,
SHE WAS POISON IVY 24/7.
WELL, WHEREVER HE PUT HER
OBVIOUSLY CONTAINED HER, RIGHT?
MAYBE THE KEY IS FIGURING
OUT HOW HE DID THAT.
WELL, THIS IS BEFORE MY TIME,
BUT FROM WHAT HE TOLD THE PRESS,
HE PUT HER IN A PLACE
NO ONE WOULD EVER FIND HER.
IT DOESN'T EVEN AFFECT
YOU ANYMORE, DOES IT?
WHAT DOESN'T AFFECT ME?
OH. BEING SECOND FIDDLE TO
WHATEVER OTHER DRAMA'S
GOING ON IN RYAN'S LIFE.
WOW. UH, YOU KNOW WHAT'S FUNNY?
I DON'T THINK WE ACTUALLY
NEED YOU HERE ANYMORE, ALICE,
SO IF YOU'D LIKE TO GO SNIFF
YOUR FLUFF AND FOLD,
NOW WOULD BE A GREAT TIME.
ARE NEITHER OF YOU CONCERNED
THAT OUR LEADER BATWOMAN LEFT
HER BESTIE INFECTED,
VULNERABLE, TERRIFIED
TO GO "HELP" A WOMAN
WHO LITERALLY SHARES A BEDROOM
WALL WITH A SERIAL KILLER?
- SHE KNOWS WHAT SHE'S DOING.
- HA HA HA!
OH, I KNOW SHE KNOWS
WHAT SHE'S DOING,
BUT DO YOU
KNOW WHAT SHE'S DOING?
UH-UH.
SEE, RYAN DOESN'T CARE
ABOUT PROTECTING SOPHIE
FROM VIRGIL. NO.
SHE CARES ABOUT PROTECTING
VIRGIL FROM SOPHIE,
SPECIFICALLY HIS SECRETS
PRESUMABLY BECAUSE
THEY'RE ABOUT HER MOTHER,
THE WOMAN WHOSE NEEDS
SHE ONCE AGAIN PRIORITIZES
OVER THE BATTEAM.
- RYAN WOULDN'T DO THAT.
- SHE ALREADY DID, LUKE,
WHICH HAS ME WONDERING
IF IT'S ONLY
A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE RYAN WALTZES
INTO RENEE'S OFFICE
WITH MARY IN BATCUFFS.
ARE YOU JOKING?
RYAN WOULDN'T ARREST
HER BEST FRIEND.
SHE... SHE'S GONNA FIND
A WAY TO FIX THIS.
HYAH!
GOOD MORNING, SUNSHINE.
I WAS WONDERING
WHEN YOU'D COME OUT TO PLAY.
YOU FIGURED OUT SUNLIGHT
WAS MY TRIGGER.
WELL, THEY DON'T CALL ME
A SUPERVILLAIN FOR NOTHING,
BUT BATTY WILL BE HOME SOON,
SO I HOPE YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
WHY ARE YOU HELPING ME?
WELL, WHY DOES
ANYONE HELP ANYONE?
TO ACCRUE FAVORS OWED,
BUT UNTIL I REDEEM THIS ONE,
I NEED YOU TO BE CAREFUL.
ONCE YOU SLITHER
OUT OF THIS BATCAVE,
RENEE MONTOYA'S GONNA
BE HUNTING YOU DOWN
LIKE A GARDNER
WITH A WEED WHACKER.
MONTOYA.
OH, HI. SOMEONE TOLD ME
TO CALL THIS NUMBER
WITH A POSSIBLE TIP
ABOUT A POISON IVY SIGHTING.
WHERE ARE YOU?
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
GOTHAM CITY BOTANICAL GARDENS.
RENEE MONTOYA.
MARY.
YOU NEED TO GET OUT OF HERE.
IT'S NOT SAFE.
TRUST ME I'M WELL AWARE.
NOWHERE AROUND YOU
IS SAFE, RENEE.
WHO ARE YOU?
I'M THE ONE WHO
CALLED IN THE TIP.
VIRGIL'S DEAD, ALICE.
I HOPE YOU'RE HAPP...
LUKE?
- LUKE!
- HEY. YEAH. I'M OK.
WHAT HAPPENED? DID ALICE
DO SOMETHING WITH MARY?
- SUNLIGHT.
- WHAT?
SUNLIGHT IS HER TRIGGER.
SHE'S NOT MARY ANYMORE.
WHERE DID YOU GET INFECTED?
THE PARK, THE RIVER?
WHERE WAS THE VINE, MARY?
IT'S NOT A HOMING PIGEON
FOR THE BROKENHEARTED, RAY-RAY.
YOU DON'T WHISPER,
"PAMELA ISLEY,"
INTO THE LEAVES AND FOLLOW
AS IT SLITHERS ITS WAY
TO HER SECRET BURIAL SITE.
YOU KNOW ABOUT PAM?
ENOUGH TO KNOW THAT SHE
DOESN'T WANT YOU TO FIND HER.
LOOK. YOU NEED TO COME WITH ME
SO I CAN GET YOU HELP.
IS THAT WHAT I NEED?
DID YOU USE THAT
SOFT, GENTLE TONE
TO LURE POISON PAM
INTO CAPTIVITY?
NO. SHE WAS OUT OF CONTROL.
YOU'RE NOT THERE YET.
LET'S KEEP IT THAT WAY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK SHE
THINKS ABOUT DOWN THERE?
I MEAN... BESIDES FREEDOM
AND WATER AND HOW HER VEINS
SCRAPE TOGETHER LIKE SANDPAPER?
EASY. LET'S NOT MAKE THIS UGLY.
SHE THINKS ABOUT HOW MUCH
SHE HATES YOU, RENEE.
MARY, COME WITH ME NOW,
AND NO ONE WILL GET HURT.
OR I STAY, AND ONLY YOU DO.
MARY, PLEASE DON'T DO THIS.
AAH!
MARY'S PHONE JUST PINGED
AT THE OLD GOTHAM
BOTANICAL GARDENS.
I NEED TO GET THERE.
- COMING WITH YOU.
- I THOUGHT YOU SAID
YOU WEREN'T READY
TO WEAR THE SUIT.
ACTUALLY, MY DAD DECIDED THAT.
I MAY NOT BE READY
TO WEAR THE SUIT,
BUT I'M NOT READY
TO LOSE MARY EITHER.
MY DAD WILL UNDERSTAND,
AND IF NOT,
I'M SURE I'LL HEAR
ABOUT IT ON THE WAY.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
I'M READING SOME
SORT OF ENERGY HERE.
YEAH. DEFINITELY PICKING UP
ONE ABNORMALLY HIGH
THERMAL PRESENCE
IN THESE TREES.
DO YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE BEING WATCHED?
TINY BIT.
YELLOW ROSES?
YELLOW ROSES
SYMBOLIZE FRIENDSHIP.
MARY KNOWS US
BETTER THAN ANYONE.
SHE KNEW WE'D TRACK HER PHONE.
YOU THINK SHE WANTED
US TO FIND HER?
I THINK SHE WANTED
TO DRAW US OUT.
- UNH!
- AAH!
BATWOMAN TO BATWING.
BATWING, WHERE ARE YOU?
YOU GOOD?
ACROSS THE DOME.
MY SHOULDER'S JACKED.
SHE CAN'T BE FAR.
STAY ALERT.
HEY. WHAT'S UP, DAD?
NO COMMENT
FROM THE PEANUT GALLERY?
I JUST GOT MY ASS
BLOWN OFF MY FEET,
AND YOU GOT NOTHING TO SAY, HUH?
DAD? DAD, YOU THERE?
WHAT KIND OF HERO
STILL NEEDS HIS DADDY?
EAST GARDEN.
I FOUND MARY... I THINK.
PLEASE. YOU DIDN'T FIND ME.
I FOUND MYSELF, AND HERE I AM.
WE'RE GONNA FIND A
WAY TO FIX THIS, MARY.
WE'RE GONNA HELP YOU.
EVERYONE KEEPS SAYING THAT.
THEY'RE GONNA HELP ME.
HELP ME WHAT...
BE LESS HAPPY,
LESS MYSELF, LESS ALIVE?
THIS ISN'T YOU, AND YOU KNOW IT.
YOU'RE NOT HEARING ME, LUKE.
THIS IS EXACTLY ME
JUST WITHOUT THE PART THAT
DOES EVERYTHING YOU WANT.
DAD, DAD, HELP! HELP ME!
YOUR DAD'S GONE, LUKE.
I TOOK OUT YOUR FAILSAFE
AND THE AI THAT CAME WITH IT.
I FIGURE LUCIUS FOX'S
BRAIN COULD REALLY
OPEN UP SOME DOORS
FOR ME IN THE FUTURE.
THAT'S MY DAD!
YOU DON'T NEED HIM.
YOU SAID IT YOURSELF.
YOU DON'T HAVE PTSD.
YOU DON'T NEED A TEAM DOCTOR,
AND YOU CERTAINLY
DON'T NEED YOUR DADDY
TELLING YOU WHAT YOU CAN
AND CAN'T DO, AM I RIGHT?
WELL, WELL, WELL.
I FINALLY HAVE
YOUR FULL ATTENTION.
I'VE BEEN A CRAPPY FRIEND.
I'M SORRY, MARY.
FRIEND? YOU NEVER
ASK NE HOW I AM.
YOU NEVER GIVE ME
ANY OF YOUR TIME.
YOU GIVE MORE OF
YOURSELF TO A WOMAN
WHO LITERALLY GAVE YOU AWAY
AND SAID SHE WANTED
NOTHING TO DO WITH YOU
THAN YOU DO YOUR OWN TEAMMATE!
AND THAT IS NOT FRIENDSHIP.
OK. MARY, WE NEED TO GO NOW.
LOOK. THESE COPS WON'T
CARE WHO YOU ARE
OR WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU.
THEY WILL JUST LOCK
YOUR ASS UP FOR GOOD!
- MARY, COME WITH ME!
- I'M DONE WITH TEAM SPIRIT!
IT'S TIME YOU HEARD
MY VOICE FOR ONCE
LOUD AND CLEAR.
MARY! MARY!
YOU'VE BEEN SO WRAPPED UP
IN YOUR OWN DRAMA, RYAN.
MARY!
IT'S TIME YOU GOT
WRAPPED UP IN MINE FOR ONCE.
ALL RIGHT. DON'T FLINCH.
LET ME HELP.
YOU CALLED THE COPS?
YOU KNEW WHO WE WERE LOOKING
FOR ALL ALONG, DIDN'T YOU?
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
MARY'S OUR BEST FRIEND.
NO. YOU TWO DON'T UNDERSTAND!
YOUR BEST FRIEND IS CURRENTLY
THE MOST DANGEROUS
PERSON IN GOTHAM,
AND YOU JUST SET HER
LOOSE ON THIS CITY.
YOU NEED A HAND?
I NEED A MARY.
I THOUGHT... I COULD
RECONNECT WITH MY FAMILY
AND HANDLE BAT DUTIES,
BUT... I BECAME OBLIVIOUS
TO WHAT WAS GOING ON WITH MARY.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
WORSE... THAT SHE FELT THAT WAY
OR THAT WE DIDN'T REALIZE IT.
SHE MAY BE INFECTED
WITH POISON IVY,
BUT THAT ANGER WAS ALL HER.
I DON'T THINK AN APOLOGY'S
GONNA FIX THIS.
EVERYTHING SHE SAID
TO ME WAS TRUE.
SHE TRIED TO TELL ME ABOUT
AN INCIDENT AT THE PARK,
AND I WAS SO DISTRACTED
WITH MY FAMILY DRAMA
I DIDN'T EVEN GIVE
HER THE TIME OF DAY.
THIS IS MY FAULT.
WHAT'S THE DAMAGE?
TORN ROTATOR CUFF. I DESERVE IT.
I DIDN'T TAKE HER WARNING
ABOUT THE SUIT SERIOUSLY.
OK. WELL, WE'RE TAKING
HER SERIOUSLY NOW.
ANY WORD FROM ALICE?
NOT YET.
YEAH. I TOLD SOPHIE
TO SHOOT ME A TEXT
WHEN SHE GETS HOME.
IN THE MEANTIME, HAVE
EVERY WAYNE SATELLITE
SCANNING FOR HER FACE 24/7
UNTIL WE FIND HER.
- OK. AND THEN WHAT?
- IT'S AN INFECTION, RIGHT?
WE'LL MAKE A CURE.
HOW DO YOU SUPPOSE WE DO THAT
WITHOUT OUR TEAM SCIENTIST?
I CALL IN A FAVOR.
♪ SHEDDING A SNAKESKIN ♪
♪ HEALING IN THE HEAT
OF THE SUN ♪
♪ I'M WATCHING...
BETTER MAKE THAT TWO.
BAD DAY?
NOT THAT I EVER NEEDED
AN EXCUSE. YOU?
YEP.
OH. HOPE I'M NOT
MAKING IT WORSE.
BELIEVE IT OR NOT, MONTOYA,
THERE ARE OTHER
PEOPLE I'D RATHER NOT
BE DRINKING WITH RIGHT NOW.
♪ AGAIN
♪ LET THE FIRE BURN
TO THE GROUND ♪
THAT'S THE NICEST THING
ANYONE SAID TO ME ALL DAY.
♪ BREATHE THE SMOKE,
BREATHE IT IN ♪
♪ DON'T STOP
UNTIL IT CLEANSES MY SINS ♪
♪ I AM REBORN
♪ OH, I AM REBORN
JADA, IT'S RYAN.
I NEED YOUR HELP.
MARY, MARY QUITE CONTRARY,
HOW DOES YOUR GARDEN GROW?
QUITE WELL IT SEEMS
FROM ALL THE SIRENS
I'VE BEEN HEARING AROUND TOWN.
IT'S FULLY ELECTRIC, STEPPY.
IS THAT SUPPOSED TO IMPRESS ME?
UH, YEAH. CONSIDERING IT WAS
10 TIMES HARDER TO HOTWIRE.
SO YOU GONNA TELL ME
WHAT YOU DID
TO EVERYONE'S FAVORITE
CELLAR DWELLER
AT THE MAYOR'S OFFICE OR WHAT?
ON THE ROAD.
AW. THERE'S THAT PATENTED
DR. HAMILTON BEDSIDE MANNER...
ALL WARM AND CHATTY.
GET IN.
♪ I AM REBORN
♪ OH, I AM REBORN
GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD!