Previously on Batwoman...
Hey, what was that
with Ryan before?
- She didn't tell you?
- Tell me what?
Doesn't matter.
I'm Poison Ivy!
You killed someone, Mary.
You thought you just flung him
out of your way, but you didn't.
He's dead.
Give me the buzzer.
I'll find a way to make it work.
I want my son back in exchange.
Fine.
By midnight, or we have a problem.
Et tu, Batwoman?
Gothamites are reeling
from the revelation
that it was the Scarlet Knight
herself
who was responsible
for unleashing Bat-villain's past
on an unsuspecting G-town.
Thanks to business queen and Jada Jet
having blown the whistle
we now know that we have
the caped crusader to thank
for the recent spate of rogues
who had plagued the city.
And while it's unclear what prompted
Ms. Jet to be so catty towards Batty
I, for one, am dying to see
how this bat spat plays out.
Bat-bar to Batwoman.
When we diverted the water
from the dam to the sewers
we didn't factor in Gotham's
crappy infrastructure.
- Bottomline it.
- Clogged sewer backed up.
It's flooding the area
around Mary's clinic.
- If the water wakes up Marquis...
- I'm on my way.
Oh, my God...
Nothing creepy about that.
I don't know what's scarier
him being gone
or what he'd left behind.
Now that I know who you are,
I know who I can hurt.
One by one.
It's all my fault.
We will get this cleaned up
as soon as we find Marquis.
I'm not talking about the clinic.
I helped Pamela do this.
I killed that man.
I told Marquis who you were.
It's okay.
No, it's not.
He can tell everyone who you are.
I've put all of our lives in danger.
So how many more people
are gonna get hurt because of me?
No! No!
That wasn't you.
That was the infection.
You understand me?
Listen to me.
You are Dr. Mary Hamilton.
You have saved so many lives, Mary.
But what about Marquis?
How are we gonna stop him?
We're gonna get that Joy Buzzer fixed
and undo the damage
that Joker did to him.
This thing spent 13 years
in cryo-freeze
and then got chucked
into the Gotham River.
Pretty sure we've voided
the warranty.
- So you can't fix it?
- No.
I mean my dad
would've studied this thing
after Batman took down the Joker.
But maybe if we had my dad's AI,
we could get some answers.
Mary.
Any idea where it is?
The night of the party,
I gave it to Marquis.
I wanted to hurt you
in the worst possible way.
So sorry, Luke.
It's okay. It's not your fault.
I know who can fix
your little buzzer.
The person who originally built it.
Meet Kiki Roulette,
the Joker's toymaker.
Her delightful creations
included the Joker's Acid Flower
his infamous Smiley Face
Nerve Gas Bomb
and that little trinket right there.
Sounds like you're a real fan.
There's nothing wrong
with admiring someone
who takes pride in her work.
There is if her work killed people.
- Hundreds of people.
- Okay, so how do we find her?
Well, that's the problem.
When the Joker...
When the Joker was
apprehended by Batman
Kiki evaded capture and disappeared.
Can you access her medical records?
That's some pretty intense eyewear.
Probably
a very specific prescription.
Good call. Rare prescription indeed.
Factoring in deterioration of age...
Yeah, okay.
Got a possible match in Drescher
for a Kathleen Rogers.
It could be an alias.
Yeah, I mean, this might be our girl.
The address is for a halfway house.
- Okay, I'm on it.
- No.
I'll go.
You should focus on Marquis.
We're talking
about enlisting the help
of an emotionally unstable terrorist
to repair frontal lobe damage
with a children's toy.
A doctor should probably be involved.
Alice, go with her.
Oh, why me?
Yeah, why her?
Because as far as Marquis knows
Alice and Mary are still Bat-enemies
which means
he won't be targeting them.
You two, on the other hand,
are still in his crosshairs.
I'm sorry, can we just
go back to the part
about not being a Bat-enemy?
I'm confused.
Okay, so, what are we supposed to do?
Lay low while I try to
track down Marquis.
Hey!
I got a better idea.
Why don't we just tell Marquis
I kissed you
and you pushed me away?
- Then I'll be in the clear, right?
- I didn't push you away.
Then what is it you think you did?
I don't know, I...
- We have bigger problems.
- Is that what we are?
- A problem?
- You know what I mean.
Actually, that's the whole point.
I don't know and you won't tell me.
I feel like...
We need to focus
on keeping Gotham safe.
We can wait for us.
Sorry, am I interrupting?
- No.
- Yes.
I was just about to suit up
to find Marquis.
Well, you're not gonna have to
look very far.
He's on every channel.
The buildings you see behind me
are where all the insanity in Gotham
is supposed to be locked up safely
and away from the public.
But I'm here to tell you
the real insanity is out there.
And it's dressed up like a bat.
What does that say about our city
that its supposed protector
is signified by a rabid bloodsucker
who moves in the shadows,
hidden from the eyes of the public?
And any accountability?
How many people have to keep paying
the price for Batwoman's insanity?
Shouldn't the city
at least know her name?
But if Batwoman
won't take responsibility
I guess I'll have to.
Somebody has to restore
the sanity to Gotham.
That's why as CEO
of Wayne Enterprises
I've entered into a partnership
with the city
and I will pour millions of dollars
into improving this notorious asylum
so that the truly ill among us,
like Batwoman
can, at last, have the professional
help they so desperately need.
Mr. Jet, what exactly are your plans
for improving mental health
in Gotham...?
Gotta be honest, that's not the way
I thought Marquis
would be led into Arkham.
And I thought
him taking over Wayne was bad.
Whatever he's got planned for Arkham
can't be good.
I don't get it.
He had all of Gotham watching
and he could've outed me as Batwoman.
It would've been so easy
to destroy me.
Maybe you're not his target.
Maybe the thing he wants to destroy
is the symbol of the Bat itself.
I don't know.
I can't help but to think
there's another reason.
Well, whatever it is,
it's got Marquis presenting himself
to Gotham as some kind of hero.
Then we need to expose him
for what he really is.
Because apparently the purple hair
and Joker couture was too subtle?
He killed a Wayne security guard,
doctors at Jeturian.
I mean, there's gotta be video.
- He's scrubbed all that.
- There must be some proof.
Somewhere.
Yeah.
And I think Jada's sitting on it.
She told me she had something
over Marquis
some kind of leverage
that kept her safe.
If it's bad enough to protect Jada...
maybe it's good enough
to protect the city.
Mr. Jet, I appreciate your generous
donation to Arkham
but I do have some concerns
about your plans
for a work-release program.
I see it as more of a
"compassionate non-confinement."
Mr. Jet,
these are dangerous criminals.
And you think locking them up
makes them any less dangerous?
How else do you expect a caged animal
to behave?
We're not talking
about stray dogs here.
And yet, that's exactly
how you're treating them.
These are sadistic rapists, Mr. Jet.
Serial murderers,
the worst of the worst.
Good.
That's exactly who I want to meet.
Victor Zsasz.
Like the hair.
I've been thinking
of growing mine out.
Marquis Jet.
Big fan of your work.
Oh, then we have something in common.
I'm a fan of my work as well.
So it's true.
You mark each of your kills
with a scar.
Consider my body my resume.
Well, from the look of it
you're probably already collecting
your pension, huh?
There's always room for a few more.
I was hoping you'd say that.
Looks like the place.
Does it ever get easier?
Living with the things you've done?
And don't say it's all my fault.
Oh, that's what the Bat-Team's
been telling you?
Yeah.
It's probably because I think
you're too emotionally fragile
to handle the truth.
Which is?
It's totally your fault.
That hunter didn't vine-hurl himself
into the tree.
And dying your hair back
to its natural color
doesn't change that.
So... So, what do I do now?
Easy.
You take all of your feelings
and you bury them deep down inside
and you cover them up with a layer
of "people die all the time"
then you sprinkle on some
"he probably did some bad stuff too."
And then you pack it down
with a nice, little bit of
"he might've even deserved it"
and then, poof, all those icky,
no-good feelings go bye-bye.
At least that's what I do.
But...
I'm not a sociopath.
Amber, I'm not the one restricting
your curfew, you are.
Privilege comes
with its responsibilities.
Now go, go see if you can help out
in the kitchen.
- Hi.
- Hello.
We're looking for one
of your residents. Kiki Roulette?
Might be going by Kathleen Rogers?
Yeah, Kiki.
She left our care some time ago,
wasn't a good fit.
Well, do you know where she went?
Honestly, we were just happy
to see her go.
Not that we don't wish her the best.
Oh, okay.
Well, thanks anyway.
Sorry to bother you.
Actually, we do mean to bother you.
Crazy knows crazy...
Kiki.
It's Kathleen now.
What are you doing?
Marquis has my dad's AI.
If he's busy playing mayor
of crazy-town
now's my best chance to get it.
If you're breaking into Wayne Tower,
I'm going with you.
Nope. Sorry. You're staying put.
I'm not gonna be responsible
for putting
whatever you are to Ryan to danger.
- We kissed. It's not important.
- You sure about that?
Fine.
I kissed her.
I thought she was into it
but then she blows me off.
Then she tries to order me to stand
down like I'm some Point Rock plebe
but I'm the only one on the Bat-Team
with an actual certification
in Special Weapons and Tactics.
Then you should be able to handle
the Line Launcher.
Saw Marquis on the TV.
It seems like he hates Batwoman
almost as much as you do.
That woman
shouldn't have provoked him.
First she abducts him
and then she loses him.
No wonder it sent him over the edge.
I don't think he needed much
of a push.
Yet you don't seem concerned
about being a target.
We have an arrangement.
Does this "arrangement"
have anything to do
with your videos
of Marquis' misdeeds?
His father died in a pretty
mysterious circumstances.
I bet you've got something
in that library
that could solve
that little whodunit.
And what if I did?
Then you need to use it. Now.
Turn it over to the authorities.
Stop protecting him.
Everything you have been afraid of
all these years
is about to happen.
If you think Marquis
is gonna let your home videos
get in the way of his revenge
you don't know your son.
Excuse me, Miss Jet?
There's a man here to see you.
He doesn't have an appointment.
Oh, my God!
But he does have a gun.
I promise, Miss Jet,
I won't take up much of your time
frankly because
you don't have much of it left.
Oh, hey, Ryan!
I'm actually glad that we ran
into each other, Ryan
because I gotta say, you have done
really well for yourself.
Much appreciated.
I meant to get you a congrats gift
after you made Wayne CEO
but by the time I got around to it,
you'd already been disgraced
and it just felt I could be
bringing up a sore subject.
But honestly, congrats, and sorry.
- You know this man?
- In another life.
"Life"! Thank you.
Man, I was really struggling
for a segue there
and you totally bailed me out.
Life, as in yours, Miss Jet,
is hanging in the balance here.
You got the evidence you came for.
I'm afraid it's a little more
complicated than that.
Then why don't I make it simple?
Whatever you're being paid,
I'll triple it.
Well...
considering your son hired me
killing you just lets him
inherit more money
that he can then give to me
so it's really just a waste
of our time, yours especially.
Well, if it's me you're after...
then you can let my daughter go.
"Daughter"?
Wait, I thought your mom was dead.
Right?
Dead Mom Number 1 died in childbirth
blah, blah, blah, foster care
and then you were adopted
by Dead Mom Number 2.
So how does that make her
soon-to-be Dead Mom Number 3?
She's not.
She's my biological mother
who didn't die in childbirth.
So after years of separation
you two actually found each other
and reconnected
only to discover that,
despite being apart,
you both stormed
the corporate CEO patriarchy
to become powerful titans
of business?
Now that's what I call
a happy ending.
Except for the part where I have
to do what childbirth didn't.
But, uh-oh, twist!
There is a chance for
a last-minute rescue.
But only if Batwoman comes
to save you.
So here's the deal.
I left s little note
on the Bat-signal.
There it is.
Apparently, your son wants
to give Batwoman
a ringside seat to your demise.
I'm not really sure what her dog is
in this fight,
but let's put an hour on the clock
anyway.
Factoring in Gotham rush hour,
that ought to give Lady-Bat
plenty of time to get here.
Of course, then she has to stop me.
The suspense might kill me
before I have to kill you.
So...
If you two have any last
mother-daughter things
you wanna discuss,
funeral arrangements perhaps,
now would be the time.
Why would you want me
to fix this thing?
It's already hurt so many people.
Because we think we can use it
to help the last person it hurt.
The little boy on the bus.
Well that little caterpillar
blossomed
into quite the psychotic butterfly.
Exactly as the buzzer was designed
to do.
The electrical impulses rendered
the part of his brain
controlling empathy dormant.
Flipped it off like a light switch.
But another zap would flip it
back on?
In theory, yes.
A jolt to a psychotic brain
would reopen those neural pathways.
Okay, great.
I need my tools to fix it.
They're all back at the Joker's
old workshop.
I've worked so hard to put
all of this behind me.
I don't wanna go back.
Oh, come on.
The only thing you don't wanna
go back to is prison.
And as someone who used to be
a huge fan of yours,
I see right through that 12-step,
safe space, Den Mother routine.
So you can drop the act.
It's not an act.
I've worked for over a decade
and a half
to find ways to make up
for the damage I've done.
Who knew fixing this awful thing
would be one of them?
You should save your time
and just shoot me.
- Batwoman's not coming.
- You think?
I don't know if you've been
keeping up with current events,
but there's a bit of bad blood
between me and her.
You too? Wow.
We have so much in common.
I mean, I didn't abandon a daughter
to the city's
brutally underfunded foster system,
all the while perched comfortably
atop a billion-dollar empire,
but, you know, potato-potato.
I didn't abandon her.
No. You just paid the doctor
$2 million to do it for you.
Now this is the content I came for.
The money wasn't to cover up
giving birth to you, Ryan.
No. It was to cover up your affair.
It's more complicated than that.
It was a different time
and I was in a different place.
I was looking at everything
that I worked for
going down the drain.
And then the doctor told me
about a couple
who were desperate to have a child
of their own and...
I saw it as an opportunity
to give you a loving home.
The 2 million was supposed to go
to the family
to ensure that you would want
for nothing.
All those years,
I thought you were being cared for
by loving parents but...
It was only when you found me
that I realized
that the doctor kept the money
for himself
and dropped you off at
a fire station.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Because I was trying
to push you away.
To protect you from Marquis.
But...
Clearly I failed on all fronts.
I just wanna thank you both
for letting me be a part
of this special moment, truly.
Thank you.
But...
It seems Batwoman is a no-show.
And I'm afraid deadline
is a deadline.
It's a very violent word
when you think about it.
But entirely appropriate
to this moment.
Ryan, any last words for Ms. Jet?
Yeah.
Mom...
Duck.
My God.
That's why Batwoman didn't show up.
She was here the whole time.
Anything I can do to help?
Yes. Keep her from touching that.
I remember you, Talky Teddy.
You were the hottest toy
of the holidays.
Every kid in class wanted one.
Little did they know, Kiki over here
had attached the pull cord
to the pin of a fragmentation grenade
hidden inside.
- How many people were...
- Killed?
Five.
Two adults, three children
and another 12 suffered
permanent injuries.
How do you move on from that?
You don't.
You live with it every day.
At least that's what my therapist
spent years
trying to get through to me.
I had all the excuses.
"It wasn't me."
"The Joker made me do it."
There's no escape from all the pain
that I caused.
My mind started to play tricks on me.
I would see my victims everywhere.
What did you do to make it stop?
Once I reach my breaking point,
my therapist insisted
that I had to do the hard work,
that I needed to accept
responsibility
for everything that I'd done.
The people I hurt
can't forget what I did to them.
So how can I?
Nice landing.
Ryan would be impressed.
Not that she'd ever show it.
She's just so hard to read sometimes.
You know one minute
I think she's into me,
the next minute,
she's shutting me out.
And you thought pulling her in
for a kiss would clear things up?
Cameras deactivated.
Honestly, I don't know
what I was thinking.
I do.
Pretty sure I know your type.
Hey, for the record,
I was into Ryan long before
I knew she was Batwoman.
Exactly how long for the record?
Not important.
You had a crush on Ryan back
when you thought she was a criminal?
We are done talking about this,
I'm not.
Pretty sure you are.
Dad? Can you hear me?
Been a while, son.
Yeah, Believe me,
I know. I'm taking you home.
Hold up.
We've got access to Marquis' laptop.
We'd be crazy if we didn't
take a peek under the hood.
Dad? Wanna help us hack a laptop?
I know a guy in my profession's
not supposed to develop feelings
for his targets,
but you two really bulls-eyed me
right here.
So where do we go from here?
Well, based on recent history,
you call up Dana Dewitt
with your latest scoop
outing me as Batwoman.
I wouldn't do that to you.
Are you sure about that?
Ever since we've met,
all you've done is take away
anything good in my like.
You came after me as CEO of Wayne,
and you came after me as Batwoman.
And you think some sob story
about how you tried to
give me $2 million
make a damn difference?
Didn't you ever wonder where I was?
How I was doing?
Did you ever even think about me?
Of course I thought about you.
Yeah.
Just not enough to check up on me.
You wanna know what I would've
wanted instead of $2 million?
A mom that cared enough
to make sure I was in good hands.
That I had someone to walk me
to school
on my first day of kindergarten.
Someone to make me cupcakes
for my birthday.
Someone to yell at me
for staying up too late watching TV.
But I had to wait 14 years
for any of that.
You're right.
And look at you.
The child I gave nothing to,
and you achieved all of this.
I gave Marquis everything,
and look how he turned out.
Maybe the greatest thing
I ever did for you
was staying out of your life.
Ryan? Marquis is using Arkham inmates
as his own personal security force.
And he's siccing Zsasz on you
and Jada.
Yeah. Already dealt with him.
But how do you know about that?
Luke and I hacked into his computer.
After we broke into Wayne Tower.
- You what? I told you to lay low.
- And I didn't listen.
Because I don't have to.
You're not my keeper.
And you're not my anything.
No, just someone
trying to keep you safe.
Fight about it later.
We got bigger problems.
According to his call log
Marquis has been in contact
with Kiki Roulette.
-You got it working again?
-Yes.
But the circuit board's so corroded,
buzzer's only got one zap left in it.
And that's the good news.
Which would seem to imply
there's bad news.
Oh, it's bad. It's really bad.
Because you see,
now that this thing's working,
I'm not sure how much longer
Marquis needs you alive anymore.
Right back at you.
I probably should've expected that.
And that.
Mary's not picking up.
Sophie's sending you
the GPS location of her phone.
-Batwing out.
-Let's get the hell out of there.
One second.
I want to clone the hard drive.
If I knew you were gonna be snooping,
I'd have cleared my browser history.
So everything you said
your therapist told you
about healing,
doing all the hard work,
those were all lies?
Oh, no, no, no. That was all true.
I just didn't want to do it.
But in my defense, though,
my therapist was Harleen Quinzel
so you know...
Kiks,
how's my favorite toymaker doing?
Happy to be dealt back into the game.
Well, you can thank your former
Arkham cellmate for connecting us,
and I can thank you
for getting me the Joy Buzzer.
Yeah, about that,
there's not much joy left.
Circuitry's shot. You got one buzz.
Good. That's all I need.
Boss, you better take this.
Your plan to make me witness
Jada's death didn't work out.
Well, if somebody needed a win,
it was you.
You know honestly, with all
that bad press you're getting,
I'm shocked that you even wanted
to show your face in public.
How about I give them a name
to go with it?
-What do you think they'll say then?
-Not a damn thing.
Because
you're not going to tell them.
Oh, you sure about that?
Yeah, you are too.
Because the moment you say my name,
all of Gotham will know
how much I accomplished with nothing.
and how little you accomplished
with everything.
Well, you got me there.
But you know what I've got?
Your friends.
Not to mention your sidekick
and your side-piece.
What do you want?
To do what I promised.
To hurt the people you care about
one by one.
How do you wanna do this? You...
You want to do it Alphabetically?
By birthday? By height?
Hey, Batwoman,
remember when I told you
I could take care of myself?
I meant it.
That's quite an entrance.
Don't get all impressed just yet.
I lost the buzzer.
Marquis has it now.
I just wanted you to know
so you can be ready.
There's no telling
what he has planned.
I'm sorry I wasn't able to stop him.
I'm pretty sure I'm the one
who should be saying that.
I failed him.
Just like I failed you.
I couldn't acknowledge
the love that I had for you.
So I signed a check,
and I hoped for the best.
But it doesn't mean
that I didn't love you.
Or that I didn't consider you
a part of me.
I named you after my own father.
And I did think about you. Every day.
But I had to bury those feelings
because they would have crushed me.
Which is clearly what I do
when I don't want to get hurt.
I put up a wall.
So that's where I get it from.
That's my life, Ryan.
Don't let it be yours.
Right.
Diagnostic complete.
Looks like you survived
a nightmare road trip
and a stint with a Joker fanboy.
Thanks to you, son.
I see you decided
to wear the suit again.
Yeah. Sorry about that.
- Don't be.
- Well, good. Because I'm not.
It took me a while,
but I finally realized that
I was just using the suit
to protect myself
from the things
I didn't want to face.
So you figured it out, you
didn't need the suit to be a hero.
I knew you'd get there, Lucas.
Thanks, Dad.
But you couldn't have told me
that sooner.
Any other thoughts
you'd like to share?
Just one. I'm proud of you.
They say you should never meet
your heroes.
What do they say
about meeting your villains?
I'm sure
they'll say we make a great team.
And with one buzz left.
Who's gonna get the last laugh?
Alice?
It's me.
You can come out now. I'm alone.
What's with all the black?
Where did you come from?
It's actually for where I'm going.
The wake. For the hunter.
The man that I killed.
Oh, my goodness
that touchy-feely terrorist really
did a number on you, didn't she?
Please tell me you're not taking
life advice from a woman
who puts hand grenades
in teddy bear tummies.
It doesn't mean that she is wrong.
No, it means she cocooned explosives
inside a fuzzy symbol of kindness
that children
instinctively want to hug.
And if I don't take responsibility
for all of the pain
that I have caused
and do the hard work to make amends,
then I am no different than her.
Kiki really sent you on a guilt trip,
huh?
And look, she even packed you a bag.
Actually, this is for you.
With your immunity deal
gone bye-bye
I packed this much
of your stuff as I could fit.
There's cash in there too.
Enough to get you far away from here.
Yeah...
I can't leave Gotham just yet.
What possible reason
do you have to stay?
Everyone is hunting you, Alice.
I know. But...
what if I wasn't Alice?
I don't want to be her anymore.
I don't want to be a sociopath.
Oh, my gosh.
This is huge.
I can help you.
I was hoping you'd say that.
Because I'm not really the kind of
gal who likes to do the hard work.
Then what do you want?
That Joy Buzzer.
We need the buzzer for Marquis.
But you have a sister
who needs it more.
Look, if you brought me down here
to lecture me
I don't tell you when to be Batwoman
and you can't tell me
what I can and can't do.
- I'm not your sidekick.
- It's not about that.
Well, then if it's about you
wanting to protect me.
I am not your damsel to rescue.
I know.
It's not about that, either.
Then what is it about?
It's about me being real with you.
I keep people at arm's length.
I've lost a lot of people in my life
and I'm scared to death
to lose anyone else.
So I don't let people in
and the whole superhero thing
gives me the excuse
to keep doing that.
I get it.
I won't push.
You don't have to.
I'll buy you a new one.
I hate that thing.
Yup.