No!
- Stop!
- This is terrifying.
They released this to the public?
Keep your nasty feet
on your side of the couch.
Fine. Jeez.
- You call yourself a roommate.
- No, I don't.
I'm a military-trained babysitter
who makes sure
you're receiving your proper meds.
Did you hear that?
Someone's on the balcony.
You drank my pinot?
I was saving that.
I'm sorry.
It didn't have your name on it.
It's my damn house.
Assume everything
has my name on it.
Do you want the psychotic slasher
out there to hear us?
On three.
One, two, three!
- The door was locked.
- What's going on?
I'm here for her. Get dressed.
Oh, actually, I'm super comfy here
in Sophie's ex-husband's
really cool sports tee.
Renee intercepted some 911 call with
a lead on a possible Rogue weapon.
Get your ass dressed.
Well, this certainly makes snuggling
with Sophie same same.
Can you have a little respect
and help me get him down?
Why are we rushing?
I'm pretty sure he's dead already.
Yeah, well...
It's only a matter of time
before DCPD shows up
and takes our evidence.
Please tell me we don't have
to recover his undies.
Just the bindings.
Renee thinks the culprit
used Catwoman's bullwhip.
As in one of the Bat trophies?
Well, this was easy. Found it.
Can I please go back
to my movie night now?
I don't think
this is Catwoman's whip.
I don't care
if it belonged to Indiana Jones.
If Renee thinks it is, let her,
so she can cross
another weapon off her list
and I can be one step closer
to earning my freedom.
According to Luke,
Catwoman and Batman had a thing.
A thing? So much leather.
- How did that work?
- Well, for her...
She apparently stole
some of Batman's nanotech
and wove it into her whip
making it indestructible.
This looks like it was cut
with a pocket knife.
I'll have someone from Mary's clinic
pick up the body
so she can do
a thorough exam.
You need to figure out
who killed this guy.
- And you, partner?
- I have dinner plans.
Renee literally has these missions
hanging over our heads.
Who could possibly be more important?
Someone who has much more
hanging over mine.
My mother.
No, Mrs. Baxter.
I did not use your investments
to fund a luxury music festival.
Wayne stock is down 53%
and our crisis management team
just quit.
As CEO, I urge you
please ignore the tabloids.
- I told you, I will fix this.
- Yeah. Okay.
When? The company is in the red
for the first time ever
and you've been
on non-stop damage control
for the last three days.
What is this?
Uh, roomie, when you took out
the trash this morning, you clearly
forgot to dump out
Jada's dinner party invitation.
It came by courier yesterday.
Of course, she turns an easy email
into a massive carbon footprint.
She just tanked Wayne.
Why would she ever think
that you'd wanna go?
I guess we'll find out, won't we?
You're going?
Alice found evidence linking
Jeturian to Black Glove.
Alice, who is literally
hallucinating so badly
that we had to pull her
out of an insane asylum.
Okay. Look, we need
to find something
to hang over Jada's head
like she has over mine.
Until then, she we will always
have us at her mercy.
We need a smoking gun.
So we bug her office,
see what we find out.
She's not inviting you over
to show you her silk linens, Ryan.
She has an agenda.
And if she was able to uncover
Wayne's hidden accounts...
Sorry. What was I saying?
If she was able to uncover
Wayne's hidden accounts...
Exactly. Then who's to say she can't
uncover your hidden identity too?
You're right. I need to be careful.
Which is why I'm bringing backup.
- So you're Ryan's date?
- So saw that coming.
It's not a date. It's recon.
But you're wearing a push-up bra,
so it's a date.
You know this is your fault, right?
Don't blame me
for this repulsive love affair.
If you'd never told Ryan
that her biological mother
was still alive,
we wouldn't be in this mess.
Soph, the guilt I think
I'm supposed to be feeling
is seriously killing
my hallucination-free vibes.
Seriously, for the last three days
it's just been me, myself, and I.
The meds are working.
Crazy Alice is crazy no more.
Don't poke the bear.
Tell me that you hear that.
It's your phone.
It's Montoya.
Seriously, people, I am on vacation.
Oh, no.
You're a criminal
who's on work release.
And she said to get your ass
to her office now.
May I offer you a beverage
while you wait?
The Madam recommends
a 1994 Cote des Blancs.
We're good.
Very well.
Madam Jet will be down shortly.
"Madam Jet will be down shortly."
Is she for real?
As real as the bling
in her chandelier.
I feel like the foster kid
who isn't allowed to sit on anything.
That's the point.
This is an intimidation move
to get in your head.
Make you think you have nothing
and she's got everything.
Shouldn't be too hard considering
my last address was my license plate.
Ryan, I'm glad you could come.
Oh, I see you brought a friend.
Girlfriend, actually.
Sophie. Nice to meet you.
- You as well.
- Sorry to interrupt, Madam.
The chef assures me
he has things covered here.
Great. Good night, Damien.
On your way out,
would you please inform him
that we'll be having another?
Yes, Madam.
Chef, the Madam has requested
preparations for another guest.
Oh, the more the merrier.
There, there, little pig.
Time for the professor
to teach the class how to squeal.
So how did you two meet?
- Through friends.
Was it a Tuesday?
Definitely, because it was, uh...
Taco night.
And you offered to buy me a drink
to wash down
- the chips.
- The chips.
Uh, you know...
You know, when the corner
of a chip gets stuck
in the back of your throat?
Yeah. Just the coughing,
choking, watery eyes.
I mean, I think
there was sweat involved.
- Sounds romantic.
- It wasn't cute.
But that's the point.
I mean, someone sees you
at your not-cutest
and still asks you out.
I mean, at the end of the day,
we just want someone who's loyal.
I know that if I were dying,
Sophie would
sit beside me, put her arms around me
and tell me everything will be okay.
Excuse me. Bathroom?
Last room down the hall.
We should all be so lucky.
That was beautiful.
Yeah.
Now let's get ugly.
Why am I here?
If this is your olive branch
for destroying my company,
you're gonna need a damn orchard.
I couldn't have been more clear
when I told you to stay away
from my family.
And now I'm in your living room,
so, what the hell is going on?
Whatever is going on between you
and Marquis needs to stop.
- Who says something's going on?
- A mother always knows.
Now I need you to ask your girl
to leave so I can get real with you.
Get real?
Rich coming from the woman
who convinced me she was dead.
Dying will be the easy part, Ryan,
for you and a lot of folks
if you don't do exactly what I say.
Yo! Nobody at the door?
Where's my man, Damien?
You never know what kind of a psycho
might come waltzing into this place.
Marquis, what are you doing here?
Heard there was a family dinner.
- Batcave?
- Copy. Are you in?
Ten bedrooms and 15 bathrooms later,
I found her study.
Okay. Good. Find somewhere central
away from A/C vents, shredders,
anything that creates noise.
All right.
I'm at her desk. Fire it up.
Testing. One, two, three.
All right. We are up.
Now get out of there.
I will. In two seconds.
Sophie, I strongly suggest
that you get out of there.
Looks like Ryan wasn't the only one
cut out of the family.
I'm gonna send you a face
to run through rec.
Uh, go for it. Standing by.
Sophie?
Luke? Do you copy?
Hey! Hey! Sophie!
Luke, do you copy?
The powder room's
on the first floor, honey.
Big house. Got lost.
Dinner's ready.
We're supposed to have
a secret partnership
and you're sitting
there having secret dinners with her.
Whose side are you on?
I hate to break it to you,
she already knows
about the partnership.
How?
Can we please eat
before any more guests arrive?
So she doesn't think it's a trophy.
Something about Batman and Catwoman
between the sheets.
Personally, I didn't think
heroes did that sort of thing
but, uh, what do I know,
I'm a villain.
Then prove me wrong.
This is a record of every Rogue
that's tormented Gotham.
If it's not a Catwoman wannabe
then use that beautifully
demented mind and tell me
who would string up a naked man
in an auto shop with a bullwhip?
Magpie. Not possible.
Too many shiny piercings
left on the victim.
Shelly Gaynor aka The Whip.
Sounds promising.
Nope. Animal advocate.
Her whip was faux leather.
Oh, this one is kinkier
than a garden hose
but, um, Talia Al Ghul
is far too impatient
for performative victim staging.
I think we found our girl.
Manipulative,
obsessive, backstabbing.
Who is she?
You.
What's with your creepy obsession
with Poison Ivy?
What are you talking about?
Your case files
on everyone else are anemic.
But this one on Pamela Isley
reads like you're planning
on writing a biopic.
Juicy interviews,
detailed facts sheets.
A confidential
psychological evaluation.
Now you need you to prove me wrong.
Are Batwoman and I looking
for these weapons of mass destruction
to stop criminals?
Because I think
that you brought us together
to find one viney vixen
in particular.
Anybody else feel a little sorry
for that thing?
Roasted suckling is considered
a delicacy in most of the world.
I'm vegan, so it doesn't matter
which continent my ass is on.
I'm not touching that.
Perhaps more wine
will enhance the experience.
Our esteemed chef flew
from Metropolis to cook for us.
He comes highly recommended.
So, if I may,
you're the estranged daughter
who just recently bonded
with your brother?
Well, that's bad because he has
a co-dependent relationship
with his mother
who now sees you as a threat
to her relationship with her son.
Zoey's dissertation
is on modern family dynamics.
Particularly
Triangulation as it relates
to Bowen's Family Theory paradigm,
rescuer, victim, persecutor.
That's interesting.
Does Bowen have a term
for backstabbing sisters?
I need the ladies.
Tannins go right through me.
Backstabbing sisters?
I wasn't the one who orchestrated
this whole dinner.
Jada did.
Was that what you wanted?
Marquis finds out I'm having dinner
with his mom so he stops trusting me?
If we're going to have a conversation
about trust, let's talk about
what your girlfriend thought
she was going to find in my study.
Exactly. So don't talk to me
about having an agenda.
You're right, Jada.
I did come here with an agenda.
I came to say thank you.
Thank you for giving me up.
Thank you for walking away
and letting me
be someone else's problem.
Because I didn't get the butlers
or the five-course meal,
or the mansion.
I got a home. I got love.
I got a real mother.
Should have known, Zoey.
Wine and family drama do not mix.
Why can't I feel anything?
Turn the faucet, Zoey.
Gotta say,
I'm not about to let my baby sister
win best speech of the night.
Marquis, haven't we had
enough theatrics for one evening?
Don't worry. I'll keep it simple.
To family and loyalty.
You okay?
I can't feel my arms.
Relax.
Just a little paralytic.
Okay. Maybe a lot of paralytic.
Get away from us.
You're not an easy woman
to get alone.
Practically had to convince you
I was royalty
to get the keys to the kingdom.
You don't remember me, Mrs. Jet?
I have no idea who you are.
Do you really fire so many people,
they're all a blur?
Lazlo Valentin.
I was a chef in the dining hall
at your office until you fired me.
Valentin. Okay. I remember the name.
Good for you!
You know what I remember?
Telling my family
"Hey, guys, no more money's
coming in for a while."
"Boss lady hates daddy's cooking
so now nobody wants
to hire him anymore." Yeah.
And I remember the divorce papers,
the debt collectors, the repo man...
Do you really think she remembers
the damn cook from the building caf?
- Marquis!
- No. You probably said
the food sucked
and your staff replaced his ass.
- It's just business, bro.
- Just business?
I lost my family because of her.
So now you'll lose yours.
You told Marquis about this dinner?
How else could you watch me
chop him into bacon bits?
But the unexpected daughter?
Talk about an amuse-bouche.
Marquis, come on.
Get up. We gotta go.
I can't... I can't move.
Zoey, she's still upstairs.
I got him. Go!
I'll find Zoey.
You guys get outside
and call for help.
I got you.
Come on.
Zoey. Zoey, we gotta go.
It won't open. Why won't it open?
He must have locked us in
from the outside.
- My phone has no service.
- Mine either.
Which little piggy went to market?
Which little piggy
should have stayed home?
Upstairs. Follow me.
Go. Go without me.
No. Marquis, come on.
You can do this. Let's go.
A lesson from Professor Pyg
nobody likes an uninvited guest!
Come on. Come on!
I'll huff and I'll puff,
and burn your house down!
He's gone.
For now.
Zoey's dead.
Oh, my God.
And he's not leaving this house
until we are too.
- What is this place?
- It's a panic room.
I converted one of my closets
a few years back.
You must have a lot of enemies.
Secret closet space and all.
Signal's dead.
I had a call drop earlier.
He must have activated
some sort of signal blocker.
Tell me you have a gun in here.
I don't believe in guns.
What's wrong, not torturous enough?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Everyone just chill, okay?
Someone will eventually realize
we're missing
and come looking for us,
we just need to hang until then.
Marquis?
Marquis? Marquis, Marquis!
Marquis!
Pamela and I met at Gotham U.
I was studying Criminal Law, she was
into Botany, complete opposites
but couldn't see a future
without the other.
Love that.
At the same time,
one of her classmates
was conducting these
obsessive experiments for his Ph.D.
He and Pam were competitive.
Both super smart, kind of nerdy.
She thought it was harmless
until one night he abducted Pam
and used her as his guinea pig.
Let me guess, that'd be Marc LeGrand?
Whatever he injected her with
was poison.
Some awful combination of things
around his lab.
Oleander, nightshade, water hemlock.
It changed her entire physiology.
Turned her
into a green-thumbed psycho.
But she didn't see it that way.
She wanted to save the planet
and that meant punishing anyone
destroying it.
Except an up-and-coming cop
shacking up with a serial killer
kind of puts a cramp
in the ol' career trajectory.
She went from compassionate
and loving
to reckless and irrational overnight.
Total personality change,
eventually, it just tore us apart.
Subtext, you chose your career
over your girl.
She was lost.
Okay? Gone emotionally, mentally.
A shell of the person I knew,
and I...
I was young,
I had no idea how to save her.
Oh, relax.
I'm not actually invested
in your love story.
So where's Poison Pam?
That's a question for Batman.
Well, she's not in Arkham.
I would know.
And boring Batman
didn't actually kill anyone.
So, unless she slithered up
Jack's beanstalk...
My theory is he hid her
under the city somewhere,
away from water and sunlight
and anyone she could hurt.
Why would Batman
bury your girlfriend alive?
Because I told him to.
This shouldn't be happening.
What shouldn't happen?
This long, sappy tangent.
Especially when there's
a potential sadist on the loose.
I'm going to go see
our medical expert
and see if she found anything
on the vic's body.
Drink the water, Marquis.
We're gonna make sure he's okay.
He drank the most,
so it's hitting him first
but it's only a matter of time
before it's all of us.
Okay, okay.
Sixty-five over thirty.
That's bad.
If it keeps dropping, he's gonna die.
He needs adrenaline.
I know.
There's none in here.
There are EpiPens.
My husband carried them
for his allergies.
- Where?
- With our camping gear.
In the basement.
Tell me there's another way
to get into the basement.
What the hell is he doing?
Building a bomb.
I'm gonna need your help.
Come on.
Lazlo?
Where are you?
Lazlo, I want a truce.
You need money? How much?
I'll give you anything you want.
Let's talk.
Lazlo? I'm sorry.
I really am.
Wasn't pretty, but she made it.
So are you really Ryan's girlfriend
or was that a lie too?
Wanna know who I really am?
I'm Jordan Moore's sister.
I'm sorry, I'm light-headed,
am I supposed to know who that is?
Your men abducted her...
and injected her with freeze serum.
Killed three of her friends,
nearly killed her.
What? What are you talking about?
Stop.
Don't tell me you didn't know
about human experiments
being conducted
by your own employees.
So was that what you were doing
in my study?
Looking for evidence?
What'd you find, Sophie?
The Anarchist Cookbook?
Look, I am sorry about what happened
to your sister
but I had nothing to do with that.
I'm not the monster
you've made me out to be.
Stay with me, son.
Mama's here.
Of course.
Okay. Okay.
Come on, Ryan. Move your arm.
Move your damn arm!
Come on!
Vic had motorcycle grease
underneath his fingernails.
I found a similar but not exact
viscous synthetic on the bullwhip.
Fascinating.
What's with the botanical garden?
Oh, did the medical board
take away your license
and leave you to the whims
of herbal medicine?
Do you know
how I saved Jordan Moore's life?
I mimicked the antifreeze synthesis
done by plants
to survive subzero temperatures.
You wanna know why?
Because plants are smarter
than humans.
They're resilient, they're intuitive.
- They give back more than they take.
- Got it.
Jeez. Sorry I asked.
Anyway, do you remember
when you were being
all hero-complex-y and told me
because you're an "official"
doctor now, it is your duty
to help me when the time comes?
Well...
that time is upon us.
The delusions are back.
Between the inmates
in Arkham, the experimental meds,
the general
mise-en-scene of captivity,
I assumed it was the asylum
that was making me crazy.
Don't get me wrong.
I have enjoyed my fair share
of disassociation.
You're talking to the girl
who convinced herself
that 12 years of sewing skin masks
was a fancy tea party.
But I was in control then.
This is different.
I'm not in control anymore.
As if what's happening isn't obvious?
You reap what you sow, Alice.
All of the murders,
the pain, the misery
that you've inflicted,
they were the seeds that you planted
for the garden you'll be buried in.
Got it.
Speaking of gardens,
where have you been frolicking?
Gotham Park.
I think I exposed myself
to whatever that thing is.
I took a sample of the vine
but I can't figure out
if it's poison oak, poison sumac,
poison hemlock.
Poison Ivy.
Let me in!
Oh, my God.
He's got Ryan.
Open this door right now!
But he wants you.
If I open this door,
I'm as good as dead.
Your lesson is that when someone
shows you who they are, believe them,
because if I'm how she treats
the people spending their days
trying to impress her, guess how
she'll treat someone
she sees as a threat!
Get away from my daughter.
Take me instead,
she did nothing to you.
Well, well, Madam Swine.
You know what your lesson is?
Perfection comes at a price.
Look out!
Incoming!
Flamingo.
Excuse me?
The bullwhip killer.
It's the flamboyant,
pink Harley-straddling psycho
Flamingo.
Victim was in a rival gang,
DNA evidence
blah, blah, blah...
science.
But the point is
if the biker boot fits...
I'll alert the victim's family
and put out a warrant
for this Flamingo.
And I guess that means
Catwoman's whip is still out there?
And I can't wait to get to that
when I'm back from Tahiti.
Because I believe that...
this buys me a week's vacation.
And what is this?
Your girlfriend.
Although she is looking
a little frail.
This is a dead cutting from her vine.
- Where did you get this?
- Does it matter?
I reunited you
with your long lost love.
To think I was confused
about Batman and Catwoman.
It matters,
because these vines don't die
unless...
Unless what?
Unless she's infected someone else.
What you thinking about?
What was for dessert.
Jada's hiding something.
I don't know what,
but I trust my gut on this.
She's lying.
Then it's time for her
to tell me everything.
I'll call you tomorrow,
tell you what I learned.
Good luck.
Great first date, huh?
Definitely memorable.
And people wonder why
I don't throw dinner parties.
You okay?
Your girlfriend left this.
Once a Crow always a Crow, huh?
I didn't know about Jordan Moore.
Your word is not good enough, Jada.
Well, it has to be.
I didn't know about Jordan...
or the experiments, or the deaths.
How could I? I'm a mother.
The whole point of all of this
was that no one else get hurt.
The whole point of what?
I'm going to tell you something.
And for your sake and for everyone
you love's sake, you need to keep it
to yourself,
you need to promise me that.
I can't.
Not until I know what it is.
Marquis is sick.
What's going on, Marquis?
What'd you get for your birthday?
A bug collector kit.
That's cool.
What are you doing
with that magnifying glass?
Melting ants.
See?
They burn up in the sun.
There was an incident
during a school field trip.
Marquis was on the bus.
It pulled up to a stoplight.
And suddenly, a man dressed like
a clown, green hair, purple suit...
big ugly smile.
He jumped on board,
took over the bus.
The Joker?
There was an encounter with my son.
The Joker had this zapper
on his hand.
- The Joy Buzzer.
- Whatever it's called.
He pressed it
against my son's forehead
and an electrical charge
went through his brain.
After that day, he was different,
dark.
Horrifying.
Marquis?
No.
Marquis has been nothing
but nice to me.
Sociopaths are charming
95% of the time, Ryan.
Mom, don't be so lame.
It's not lame to tell your dad
happy birthday.
I wrote him a card!
Sweetheart, your father's overseas
and it would mean so much to him
- if he heard it from your...
- I said no!
Specialists, neurologists,
psychologists.
I have spent millions
trying to fix him behind his back
so I could have my sweet boy again.
But no one's been able to help me.
And then I learned of cryostasis.
So you were behind the freeze serum.
I had no idea my research team
was conducting human experiments.
I just thought if I could sideline
Marquis for a while,
it would buy me some time
to find a solution.
He's going in for another bite.
How's the burger, Dad?
Delicious.
What the hell?
He's onto me.
Is that peanut butter?
What's wrong?
Peanuts!
Burger!
Franklin, where's your pen?
Where's your pen?
Why are you telling me this?
Because everything I have done...
since the day we met...
has been to protect you, Ryan.
And because I need your help.
All I want is to stop Marquis
before anyone else gets hurt.