PREVIOUSLY ON "BATWOMAN"...
MARQUIS IS SICK.
THERE WAS AN INCIDENT.
THE JOKER PRESSED
THIS GODFORSAKEN THING
TO MY SON'S HEAD AND
TURNED HIM INTO A MONSTER.
I'VE BEEN TOLD THAT
ANOTHER BUZZ COULD CURE HIM.
I AM LOSING MY MIND!
THE HALLUCINATIONS
ARE BACK.
I JUST NEED
A LITTLE EDGER
UNTIL YOU CAN GET
ME THE JOY BUZZER.
THERE'S ONLY ONE BUZZ LEFT.
RYAN NEEDS IT...
FOR HER BROTHER.
YOUR DAD PROGRAMMED
YOUR SUIT'S AI
TO SPEAK
WITH HIS VOICE?
DAD, SAY HELLO
TO MARY.
HELLO, MARY.
IT'S LIKE YOU CAN
TALK TO HIM AGAIN.
IT SEEMS BATWOMAN IS
A NO-SHOW.
MY GOD. THAT'S WHY
BATWOMAN DIDN'T SHOW UP.
SHE WAS HERE
THE WHOLE TIME.
I'M SORRY, MARY.
WHAT DID YOU DO?
WHAT IF I WERE
TO GIVE YOU SOMETHING
THAT WOULD MAKE
THE JOKER...
WISH HE WERE YOU?
LET'S HAVE SOME FUN.
♪ OH, SWEET CHILD
♪ CLOSE YOUR EYES
♪ IT'S DARK OUTSIDE
HA HA HA!
HA HA HA! HA HA HA!
♪ OH, SWEET CHILD
HA HA HA HA!
♪ CLOSE YOUR EYES
♪ IT'S DARK OUTSIDE
HA HA HA! HA HA HA!
HA HA HA!
HA HA HA HA!
EXACTLY WHERE YOU SAID
THEY WOULD BE, FUNNY MAN.
♪ IT'S DARK OUTSIDE
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHY ISN'T THIS STRONGER?
ALICE, STOP THIS.
VOLTAGE, CONDUCTOR.
THEY SAID IT WOULD WORK.
- WHY ISN'T IT WORKING?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
GETTING ALICE
OUT OF MY HEAD!
ALICE, STOP... THIS.
- THAT COULD KILL YOU.
- GIVE IT BACK!
WAIT, WAIT.
JUST WAIT.
I TOLD YOU I WOULD
HELP YOU!
AND I FOUND A PLACE.
IT'S IN SWITZERLAND,
IT'S NEAR GENEVA,
AND IT'S CALLED THE WEISSE
KANINCHEN SANATORIUM.
THEY SPECIALIZE
IN CHILDHOOD TRAUMA.
THEY CAN HELP YOU.
NO.
NO MORE CELLS.
NO MORE INSTITUTIONS.
I CANNOT BE
IN MY HEAD ANYMORE!
I WANT OUT!
PLEASE GET ME OUT.
PLEASE, PLEASE.
I CAN'T.
PLEASE!
ALL RIGHT, BATWOMAN.
WHAT'S THE PLAN?
HOW DO WE BEST HANDLE
OUR ONE WILD
AND PRECIOUS BUZZ?
MARQUIS SHOWED US
HE DOESN'T HAVE ACCESS
TO A SLIVER OF HUMANITY,
AND THANKS TO, ALICE,
HE JUST GOT CONTROL
OF THE BATCAVE,
SO HOWEVER WE GET HIM,
IT'S GOT TO BE TODAY,
AND IF THIS THING ONLY
HAS JUICE FOR ONE BUZZ,
I HAVE TO BE THE ONE
TO MAKE THE PLAY.
SO WE LURE HIM CLOSE,
AND I HIT HIM BEFORE HE
KNOWS WHAT'S COMING.
OR ALTERNATIVELY,
WE GIVE IT TO ALICE.
SORRY I'M LATE.
YOU KNOW SHE JUST GAVE
MARQUIS THE KEYS
TO THE BATKINGDOM,
RIGHT?
I JUST CAME BACK
FROM ARKHAM,
WHERE I FOUND HER
PLAYING DIY
ELECTROSHOCK THERAPY
WITH A SOCKET WRENCH.
SHE'S NOT GONNA SURVIVE
HER NEXT PSYCHOLOGICAL BREAK.
WE TRIED TO HELP HER.
ALICE MADE HER BED.
OK, MARY.
WE KNOW YOU FEEL
A CERTAIN... WHATEVER
FOR HER,
BUT THE BUZZER CREATED MARQUIS.
THE JOKER CREATED
MARQUIS,
AND IF WE'RE
SPLITTING HAIRS,
HE CREATED ALICE,
TOO.
ALICE KILLED
YOUR MOM, MARY.
DO YOU THINK
I FORGOT?
YOU THINK I DON'T
KNOW HOW BADLY
RYAN WANTS
HER BROTHER BACK
OR THAT THE FIRST TIME
ALICE EVER MET SOPHIE
SHE THREW HER OFF
A 30-STORY BUILDING?
I KNOW. IT IS NOT
LIKE THIS IS
SOME EASY DECISION
FOR ME... OR ANYONE,
BUT I BELIEVE ALICE
IS CAPABLE OF CHANGE.
SHE JUST NEEDS
A CHANCE.
COME ON. EACH ONE OF
YOU LOOKED ME IN THE EYE
A FEW WEEKS AGO,
APOLOGIZED
FOR SIDELINING ME,
AND ASSURED ME
I WOULD HAVE A VOICE
ON THIS TEAM.
THIS IS IT.
THIS IS ME USING
MY VOICE.
THIS IS... THIS IS
WHAT I WANT.
I NEED TO SAVE
ALICE'S LIFE.
I JUST GOT A LIVE URGENT
MESSAGE FROM MARQUIS JET.
YEAH, ME, TOO.
I THINK
WE ALL DID.
WHAT'S UP, GOTHAM CITY?
WE HAVING FUN YET?
MARQUIS JET HOLLERIN' AT YOU
FROM A TOP-SECRET LOCATION.
THE TIME HAS COME,
THE DAY IS HERE.
TONIGHT IS THE DAMN NIGHT.
I NEED EVERYONE
TO TAKE TO THE STREETS,
GET OUT ON YOUR BALCONIES,
JUMP UP ON YOUR CAR.
HELL, CLIMB UP
TO THE TIPPY TOP
OF YOUR CORNER CHURCH STEEPLE
BECAUSE IN 5 HOURS
ON THE DOT...
I'M GONNA BE SHOUTING
BATWOMAN'S TRUE IDENTITY
FROM THE ROOFTOPS.
SPOILER ALERT!
SHE'S NOT THE HERO
YOU THINK SHE IS.
TICKTOCK, GOTHAM.
THIS IS REALLY HAPPENING.
MARQUIS JET IS ABOUT TO
SHUT BATWOMAN DOWN FOR GOOD.
WE ARE STILL
HOURS AWAY
FROM THE BATWOMAN NAME DROP,
BUT CURIOSITY
HAS ALREADY PULLED
SOME GOTHAM RESIDENTS
TO THE STREETS,
REACTING TO CLAIMS MADE
BY WAYNE CEO MARQUIS JET
THAT HE KNOWS
THE SCARLET KNIGHT'S
SECRET IDENTITY
AND THAT WE SHOULD ALL BRACE
FOR DISAPPOINTMENT.
NO DETAILS BEYOND THAT
WERE TEASED,
BUT PUTTING A FACE TO THE NAME
WOULD CERTAINLY BE
THE END OF BUSINESS AS USUAL
FOR THE CAPED CRUSADER,
WHOSE ANONYMITY IS KEY
TO HER OWN SAFETY
AND THOSE OF HER LOVED ONES.
WHILE VARIOUS THEORIES
SURROUNDING
WHO'S BEHIND THE MASK
HAVE BEEN BOUNCING AROUND
SOCIAL MEDIA...
OH. GUYS.
TOLD YOU
SHE DOESN'T KNOCK.
I TAKE IT YOU SAW
MARQUIS' THREATS.
I BELIEVE 10 MILLION PEOPLE
SAW MARQUIS' THREATS.
HOW ON EARTH
DID HE HIJACK
EVERY PHONE, TV, AND
LIVESTREAM IN THIS CITY?
HE GOT INTO THE BATCAVE.
FROM THERE, HE FOUND
THE COMPUTER,
WHICH LED TO WAYNE'S
SATELLITE,
WHICH HE USED TO OVERRIDE
GOTHAM'S AIRWAVES.
MY DAD CREATED THE TECH
IN THE EVENT
THAT BATMAN HAD TO SEND
AN SOS TO EVERY PERSON
IN THE CITY ALL AT ONCE.
ANY CHANCE YOU CAN
TRACE THE ORIGINAL FEED
BACK TO ITS LOCATION?
WITHOUT ACCESS
TO THE BATCAVE, I WAS LUCKY
TO BE ABLE TO GET
A SCREENCAP.
WELL, THAT'S NOT
GONNA HELP US.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
DO YOU REMEMBER
HOW YOUR FATHER
ALWAYS REPEATED HIMSELF
WHEN HE GOT MAD?
- VIVIDLY. WHY?
- I CAN HEAR HIM NOW.
"JADA, JADA, JADA,
YOU LET MY BOY
"TAKE ON MARQUIS WITH A
SMARTPHONE AND A DIALUP?
MM-MM-MM."
I'M SURE MY TECH TEAM
CAN PULL
A CARRIER-GRADE ROUTER
OFF JETURIAN'S SERVER FARM.
UH... THANK YOU?
WE DON'T HAVE
A LOT OF TIME.
WE'VE GOT TO FIND
MARQUIS AND BUZZ HIM
WITH THAT JOY BUZZER.
WHERE'S RYAN?
AHEM. THAT IS SUCH
A GOOD QUESTION.
UH... WHERE'S RYAN?
RIGHT. UH, SOPHIE, DIDN'T RYAN
TELL YOU WHERE SHE WAS HEADED?
UH, YES.
I BELIEVE SHE SAID
SHE WAS RUNNING
AN ERRAND.
RIGHT. THAT'S
WHAT I REMEMBER.
ERRAND. DUH. SHE DID
MENTION AN ERRAND.
WHERE WAS IT AGAIN?
TELL ME WHY YOU
DESERVE THE JOY BUZZER.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE OUT
ENJOYING YOUR LAST FEW HOURS
OF SUPERHERO
ANONYMITY?
YEAH, I SHOULD.
INSTEAD, I'M HERE
DOING MY BEST FRIEND
A SOLID
WHILE THE PERSON
WHO ACTUALLY NEEDS IT
IS OUT THERE THREATENING
TO DESTROY
EVERYTHING I'VE WORKED FOR.
OH, YOU MEAN THE
BROTHER YOU'RE SCARED
IS TOO GOOD
TO BE TRUE?
FACE IT, RY-RY, YOU CAN
BLAME MARY ALL YOU WANT,
BUT DEEP DOWN IN THAT
LITTLE ORPHAN HEART,
YOU NEED ME
TO HAVE THAT THING.
OH, WOW. MARY WAS RIGHT.
YOU DID STOP MAKING SENSE.
OR... CHANCES ARE
YOU SPENT
THE LAST FEW MONTHS
DAYDREAMING
ABOUT WHAT IT WOULD BE
LIKE TO HAVE A NUCLEAR FAMILY.
THANKSGIVING DINNERS,
FAMILY GAME NIGHTS,
THE COMFORT OF A KIDNEY SHOULD
A NEW ONE BECOME NECESSARY.
YOUR DESPERATION'S SHOWING.
WHAT IF YOU ZAP MARQUIS
AND THAT GOOD
LITTLE BOY BURIED
BENEATH THAT TACKY
CLOWN SUIT TURNS OUT
TO BE DOING JUST FINE
WITHOUT HIS NEEDY
LITTLE SISTER?
DO YOU REALLY WANT TO
RISK GETTING YOUR HOPES UP
ONLY TO HAVE HIM LEAVE
YOU LIKE EVERYBODY ELSE?
I'M YOUR SAFE BET,
RYAN. HEH HEH.
PSYCHO OR SANE,
YOU DON'T NEED ME
TO LOVE YOU BACK.
OUR STINGRAYS CAN
SIMULATE A CELL TOWER,
AND SINCE OUR SUPERCOMPUTERS
ARE TOO BIG
TO WALK THROUGH THAT DOOR,
YOU'LL NEED THIS,
A SECURE ACCESS POINT TO THE
QUANTUM COMPUTER AT GOTHAM UNIVERSITY.
DID YOU SAY
QUANTUM COMPUTER?
YOUR FATHER HAD ME FUND
THE COMPUTER LAB IT LIVES IN.
IT SEEMS ONLY RIGHT
YOU USE IT.
GREG, TELL HERSHEL TO PULL
THE GENERATOR INTO THE ALLEY.
YES, MA'AM.
THIS PROCESSOR MAKES
THE BATCAVE LOOK LIKE
IT RUNS
ON A HAMSTER WHEEL.
WHERE WERE ALL
OF THESE RESOURCES
WHEN JADA DIDN'T THINK
WE HAD THE JOY BUZZER?
DIBS ON NOT BEING
THE ONE TO TELL HER.
ANY UPDATE FROM RYAN?
NOT YET.
SO WHAT'S IT
GONNA BE, RY-RY?
WOW. THIS WAS
A WASTE OF MY TIME.
HAVE A NICE LIFE, ALICE.
I DON'T DESERVE
THE JOY BUZZER, OK?
WE BOTH KNOW THAT'S WHAT
YOU WANTED TO HEAR...
BUT I DO HAVE A LITTLE
PIECE OF INFORMATION
YOU'RE GONNA NEED IF YOU
WANT TO LIVE TO SEE TOMORROW.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
DARE I SAY IT'S
ACCURATE TO ASSUME
THAT MARQUIS IS
HARBORING A...
WEE, LITTLE MAN CRUSH
ON THE JOKER?
GOT A HIT. HONING IN
ON MARQUIS' LOCATION NOW.
HOW DOES THAT
MAKE SENSE?
WHAT ARE ALL
OF THOSE?
HIS SINGULAR CELL I.D.
IS PINGING OFF
10 DIFFERENT SHOPS
IN GOTHAM SQUARE.
ACCORDING
TO YOUR BROTHER,
WHEN HE WAS 7, THE
JOKER JUMPED ON HIS BUS
AND WHISPERED
HIS BIG, EVIL PLAN
TO DESTROY GOTHAM CITY
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
UNFORTUNATELY
FOR THE JOKER,
BATTY STOPPED HIM AND
DUMPED HIM INTO ARKHAM
BEFORE HE COULD
PULL IT OFF,
BUT, UM, CURIOUS CATHY
OVER HERE
WANDERED DOWN TO THE CAF
AND ASKED A FEW
OF THE ARKHAM LIFERS
IF MR. SMILEY PANTS
HAD EVER...
TALKED ABOUT WHAT HE HAD
PLANNED ON DOING THAT DAY.
WOW. DID I EVER HEAR
THE MOST...
INTERESTING RIDDLE.
HE'S MOVING,
JUST REALLY, REALLY SLOW.
CONVERTING COORDINATES,
ADDING ALTITUDE.
HE'S NOT ON THE GROUND.
HE'S IN THE AIR.
SO, WHAT? MARQUIS
TOOK THE WAYNE JET?
WELL, IF THE WAYNE JET
MOVED THAT SLOW,
IT WOULD FALL OUT
OF THE SKY.
- NO.
- WHAT?
NO. NO! NO!
WHAT WAS IT?
TEASE THEM
WITH A RIDDLE,
GET THEM ALL OUTSIDE.
WHAT'S WET AND MELTS
AND ISN'T SNOW
BUT ENDS IN GENOCIDE?
THIS ISN'T ABOUT
MY IDENTITY, IS IT?
THAT WAS JUST THE DRAW.
THIS... IS ABOUT
THE JOKER'S DESIRE
TO PUNISH THE CITY
FOR WORSHIPING
THE BAT SYMBOL.
IT'S ABOUT KILLING
AS MANY PEOPLE
AS HUMANLY POSSIBLE
AND RIDDLING THIS CITY
WITH SURVIVORS
THAT ARE AS UGLY
AS HIM.
HOW? HOW DOES ONE PERSON
BLOW UP AN ENTIRE CITY?
HE TOOK IT. IT'S GONE.
HE MUST HAVE FOUND
THE LOCATION
OF THE SECRET AIRSTRIP
IN THE BATCAVE'S RECORDS.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
IT'S GONE? WHAT'S GONE?
THE BATBLIMP.
THE GAME'S CHANGED.
THIS ISN'T
ABOUT MY IDENTITY.
IT'S ABOUT LURING 10 MILLION
INNOCENT PEOPLE
TO THEIR DEATHS.
IN ONE HOUR, MARQUIS IS
DROPPING ACID BOMBS
OVER THE CITY
AND DESTROYING EVERYTHING
AND EVERYONE
IN ITS BLAST RADIUS,
SO WE MAY BE IN A BAR
DEALING WITH THE FALLOUT
OF BATMAN'S GREATEST ENEMY
WITHOUT A JOY BUZZER
OR TIME TO THINK STRAIGHT,
BUT WE DON'T
GET EXCUSES.
- NO ONE DIES TODAY. AM I CLEAR?
- CRYSTAL.
GOOD. ANY CHANCE YOU CAN HACK
INTO THE CONTROLS OF THE BATBLIMP?
I'VE NEVER ONCE SEEN
THE BLIMP'S INTERFACE,
BUT IT'S POSSIBLE
THE COORDINATES
ARE VULNERABLE TO
AN ISMI CATCHER.
- NEED A YES OR NO.
- I CAN'T LAND IT,
BUT I CAN PROBABLY
GET IT CLOSE.
CLOSE IS ALL WE NEED.
I NEED YOU TO DIRECT IT
TO THE GCPD ROOFTOP.
WHY? WHAT ARE YOU
PLANNING?
SO YOU CAN STOP ME?
IT'S THAT CRAZY?
LOOK AT YOU FIGURING
ME OUT ALREADY.
NO TIME FOR DETAILS.
BESIDES, I NEED YOU AND MARY
TO PUT YOUR BRAINS TOGETHER
TO GET EVERYONE IN THE CITY
TO TAKE COVER WITHOUT
INCITING A CHAOS MOB.
HOW? NOT TO THROW SHADE
ON MY OWN SEX APPEAL HERE,
BUT YOU KNOW I ONLY
HAVE, LIKE, 300 FOLLOWERS
ON SOCIALS, RIGHT?
THE BATMAN TROPHIES.
CHANCES ARE MARQUIS
CLEANED HOUSE
ON THE BATWEAPONS,
BUT HE DOESN'T HAVE ACCESS
TO THE WING
WITH THE TROPHY ROOM
WITHOUT BATWOMAN'S DNA.
- SO?
- SO BETWEEN THE MAD HATTER'S HAT
AND THE CONDIMENT KING'S
GUN, SURELY THERE'S
SOME KOOKY TOOL IN THERE
THAT CAN INFLUENCE
PEOPLE'S BEHAVIOR.
OK. LET'S
SAY THERE WERE.
HOW THE HELL DO WE
GET INTO THE BATCAVE?
I'M SURE MARQUIS
QUADRUPLED SECURITY
SINCE BATWING AND I
GOT BUSTED
BREAKING INTO WAYNE.
JADA'S REALLY NOT HAPPY
WITH ME,
BUT I MAY HAVE AN IDEA.
I'M SORRY.
WHEN YOU SAID WE'D
GET OUR FAMILY BACK,
I TRUSTED YOU.
WE WILL GET
OUR FAMILY BACK.
HOW? THAT BUZZER WAS
THE ONLY WAY TO SAVE MARQUIS.
YOU KNEW THAT,
AND YOU STILL GAVE IT AWAY.
HAVING THAT BUZZER
IN OUR POSSESSION
WOULDN'T CHANGE
THE FACT THAT A BLIMP
HOVERING OVER OUR CITY
IS ABOUT TO DOUSE
OUR STREETS WITH
THE JOKER'S ACID BOMBS.
WE NEED TO GET PEOPLE
TO SAFETY.
I HAVE CONNECTIONS, RYAN,
BUT I HIGHLY DOUBT THE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES
IS GOING TO TAKE
MY CALL.
I DON'T NEED
THE PRESIDENT.
I NEED MY MOM
TO PICK UP HER PHONE
AND GET ME WAYNE
ENTERPRISES BACK.
DO TO HIM WHAT YOU
DID TO ME.
IF IT WERE THAT SIMPLE, I
WOULD HAVE DONE IT WEEKS AGO.
MARQUIS IS SMART.
HIS ACCOUNTING IS BULLETPROOF.
AND I'M GUESSING
HE'S NOT HIDING
A BILLION-DOLLAR
VIGILANTE FUND.
NO, BUT HE IS HIDING
SOMETHING...
THE UGLY TRUTH.
JADA...
IF YOU DO MEAN
WHAT I THINK
YOU MEAN,
THERE COULD BE
SERIOUS RAMIFICATIONS
FOR YOU, TOO.
I'VE RISKED EVERYTHING
TO PROTECT MY SON AND FAILED.
IT'S TIME I TAKE A PAGE
FROM MY DAUGHTER'S HANDBOOK.
IT'S TIME TO PUT
THE CITY FIRST.
IT'S NEVER GOOD WHEN YOUR CFO
CALLS YOU AT MARTINI O'CLOCK.
YEAH.
WHO SAID THAT?
HEH. UH-HUH.
YOU THINK YOU CAN FIRE ME?
YOU AND WHO ELSE?
OH! THE DOJ. HA HA HA!
THAT'S RICH. YEAH.
HAVE FUN WITH THAT.
MARQUIS JET'S
OWN MOTHER,
BUSINESS TYCOON JADA JET,
JUST ADMITTED TO
THE DECADES-LONG FAMILY SECRET.
3 YEARS AGO, FRANKLIN JET
WAS PRONOUNCED DEAD
AFTER A FALL.
THESE ALLEGATIONS NOW
THROW THAT INTO QUESTION.
MEANWHILE, THE WAYNE BOARD
HAS UNANIMOUSLY
REAPPOINTED RYAN WILDER
TO THE CEO POSITION,
CALLING HER PREVIOUS
RESIGNATION COERCED.
THAT POSITION WOULD BE
REINSTATED IMMEDIATELY. MS...
HEH. YOU THINK I CARE
ABOUT WAYNE OR... OR... OR FAMILY
OR ANY OF YOU IDIOTS?!
DON'T YOU GET IT?
NONE OF YOU MATTER ANYMORE.
LUKE, WE'RE IN.
JADA'S PLAY WORKED.
WAYNE TOWER WAS
POSTAPOCALYPTIC.
SO... READY TO TEACH ME
HOW TO DO THIS?
LUKE? HELLO?
BATCAVE TO LUKE.
YEP. I COPY.
JUST FURIOUSLY HACKING
INTO A NUCLEAR BATBLIMP
FROM A BARSTOOL.
APOLOGIES
FOR THE 3-SECOND DELAY.
OK. I'M AT THE COMPUTER.
TELL ME HOW MARQUIS WAS
ABLE TO HIJACK THE AIRWAVES.
OK. ARE YOU LOOKING AT THE
SATELLITE ACCESS PORTAL?
UH, THE THING WITH THE
DOTS AND THE NUMBERS?
LET'S ASSUME YES. SO
YOU'RE GONNA GET A PROMPT.
THEN YOU NEED TO
CLAIM ACCESS
TO EACH
OF THE SATELLITES.
UH...
JUST CLICK THE BOX NEXT
TO THE SATELLITE FILE.
OK. CLICKING BOXES.
IT'S KIND OF CREEPY
HOW EASY THIS IS.
WELL, CONSIDERING I JUST HAD TO REMIND
YOU WHERE THE POWER SWITCH WAS...
OK. TEAM DOCTOR,
NOT THE TECHIE.
I'D LIKE TO SEE ONE OF YOUR
PATIENT INTAKE REPORTS.
- I MISSED THIS.
- WHAT? ME FUMBLING
OVER THIS ELECTRONIC
PAPERWEIGHT YOU CALL A COMPUTER?
US.
ME, TOO.
OK. I'M TWO CLICKS AWAY FROM
CONTROLLING GOTHAM'S AIRWAVES.
OK. COOL. WHAT DID
SOPHIE LAND ON?
THE PENGUIN'S UMBRELLA.
INDUCING GOTHAM
INTO A HYPNOTIC STATE
VIA EYE FASCINATION.
I MEAN, THAT...
THAT'S BRILLIANT.
OK. HEY. UH, GET
YOUR HYPNO ON.
I JUST GOT INTO THE BLIMP.
BATBAR TO BATWOMAN.
- JUST LANDED.
- ALL RIGHT. I'M IN.
I'M ENTERING
YOUR COORDINATES NOW.
LET ME KNOW
WHEN YOU SEE IT.
YEAH.
GOT EYES.
AH. I LOVE YOU MORONS.
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
HEY. HEY!
WHY DID WE DROP?
I HAVE NO IDEA,
MR. JET.
COMPUTER CHANGED COORDINATES
AND LOCKED ME OUT.
WELL, THEN PUT IT
IN AUTOPILOT.
I DID. NOTHING IS
WORKING, SIR.
IT'S TOTALLY DEAD.
GUESS YOU TWO
HAVE THAT IN COMMON.
LUKE, I NEED THIS THING
TO BE A LOT LOWER.
YEAH. TRYING.
SOMETHING HAPPENED.
I'M LITERALLY STARING
AT A TICKING CLOCK HERE.
YEAH. I LOST ACCESS.
EVERYTHING JUST DROPPED OFFLINE.
I NEED SOME TIME
TO GET BACK IN.
WE DON'T HAVE TIME.
WISH ME LUCK.
WHOA, WHOA, HEY, HEY!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
TAKING THE SCENIC ROUTE.
LORD, HELP ME.
I'M IN THE CARGO HOLD NOW.
WHAT DO YOU SEE?
PLEASE TELL ME
THEY TAUGHT YOU
HOW TO DISARM A BOMB
AT POINT ROCK.
GET ME EYES ON IT.
HALF A DOZEN DRUMS.
ALL ATTACHED TO A TIMER
THAT TELLS ME
WE HAVE LESS
THAN 15 MINUTES
BEFORE MARQUIS MAKES IT
RAIN ACID ALL OVER GOTHAM.
WHERE DO I START?
- YOU DON'T.
- OK. I WAS EXPECTING SOMETHING
MORE LIKE
CUT THE GREEN OR PURPLE.
I COUNT AT LEAST
4 TRIPWIRES
THAT WOULD SET
THIS OFF EARLY,
NOT TO MENTION ANY OTHER
NASTY HIDDEN SURPRISES
THE JOKER MIGHT HAVE
LEFT BEHIND.
YOU TOUCH ANY ONE
OF THOSE WIRES,
THE WHOLE DAMN THING
COULD GO.
WHERE THE HELL ARE WE
WITH EVACING THE CITY?
I'M JUST ABOUT TO ACCESS
WAYNE SECURITY MAINFRAME
AND DROP A HOT TIP... NOW.
GET UNDERGROUND IMMEDIATELY.
TAKE COVER.
WAIT FOR INSTRUCTIONS.
GET UNDERGROUND IMMEDIATELY.
TAKE COVER.
WAIT FOR INSTRUCTIONS.
GET UNDERGROUND IMMEDIATELY.
TAKE COVER.
WAIT FOR INSTRUCTIONS.
GET UNDERGROUND IMMEDIATELY.
TAKE COVER.
WAIT FOR INSTRUCTIONS.
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S WORKING.
THE PENGUIN'S UMBRELLA IS ACTUALLY
HYPNOTIZING PEOPLE TO TAKE COVER.
YOU HEAR THAT,
BATWOMAN?
WE'RE MAKING PROGRESS.
YOU OUT OF THERE YET?
I'M GONNA TRY TO REROUTE
THE BLIMP OVER THE OCEAN.
OK. TELL ME YOU LEARNED
HOW TO WIRE
A BLIMP'S CONTROLS
AT POINT ROCK.
PRETTY SURE PILOT A GIANT
COMBUSTIBLE BALLOON WASN'T
OFFERED
IN BASIC TRAINING.
THIS THING BLOWS,
ACID'S STILL GONNA RAIN DOWN
OVER THE CITY.
ONCE MARQUIS REALIZES
WE TOOK AWAY HIS AUDIENCE,
HE COULD TRIGGER THE
BOMB AT ANY MOMENT
WITH YOU STILL
INSIDE.
I CAN'T JUST WALK
AWAY FROM THIS.
I'M NOT LOSING
YOU, RYAN!
YOU DON'T GET TO PLAY
THE CRAZY CARD WITH ME.
I'M NOT LOSING YOU.
NOBODY'S EVER SAID
THAT TO ME BEFORE.
AND NOBODY
EVER WILL AGAIN.
SHOULD HAVE KNOWN
YOU HAD SOMETHING TO DO
WITH WHAT'S GOING ON
BELOW.
SEE, THIS IS WHY I NEVER
WANTED A LITTLE SISTER.
THEY RUIN ALL THE FUN.
YOUR DEFINITION OF FUN IS
BLOWING UP HALF OF GOTHAM?
WHOA. WHY
SO PESSIMISTIC?
THAT MEANS HALF
THE ISLAND LIVES
TO REMEMBER THE DAY
THAT THE BATBLIMP
DISFIGURED THEM
BEYOND RECOGNITION
AND BATWOMAN DIDN'T
SAVE THEM.
ERR! UNH!
DISARM THE BOMB.
EVERYONE'S TAKEN COVER
ALREADY.
- YOUR PLAN FAILED!
YOUR PLAN TO WEASEL
IN ON MY LIFE
AND STEAL MOMMY AWAY?
HARD FAIL, SIS!
DISARM THE BOMB, MARQUIS!
W-W-WHAT IS THIS,
YOUR LAST ATTEMPT
TO WIN JADA'S LOVE?
HUH? YOU... YOU SAVE
HER SCREWED UP SON
AND THEN MAYBE
SHE'LL APOLOGIZE
FOR LEAVING YOU
IN A DROPBOX?
SHE DOESN'T
LOVE YOU, WILDER!
TAKE THE HINT!
♪ CRY
♪ I COULD BURN THE CITY DOWN
♪ I COULD PUT YOU UNDERGROUND
♪ MAKE THE STARS
FALL FROM THE SKY ♪
♪ MAKE THE CLOUDS
AND HEAVEN CRY ♪
♪ I COULD BURN IT ALL DOWN
I'M NOT DOING THIS
FOR JADA.
RIGHT. THE HERO'S
BURDEN. I FORGOT.
YOU'RE DOING THIS
FOR MANKIND!
I'M DOING IT
FOR MY FAMILY.
HA HA HA HA HA HA!
GIVE ME MY BROTHER BACK!
GIVE... HIM... BACK!
PLEASE. I WANT MARQUIS.
PLEASE!
I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY...
THAT YOU'RE SO
DESPERATE FOR A FAMILY
THAT YOU BELIEVED
YOU COULD SAVE ME!
AAH!
HA HA HA!
HA HA HA... OHH!
BATWOMAN?
RYAN? RYAN, ARE
YOU THERE? CHECK IN.
RYAN. RYAN, TALK
TO ME, PLEASE.
SAY SOMETHING.
ARE YOU OK?
YOU THINK I'M GONNA DIE
BEFORE YOU BUY ME DINNER?
UNH.
THE BOMB.
WE'RE ON IT.
♪ ANYWHERE YOU GO,
I FOLLOW ♪
♪ ANYWHERE YOU GO
♪ I FOLLOW
THIS IS WORSE
THAN I THOUGHT.
CAN YOU REWIRE
THE CONTROLS?
NOT IN TWO MINUTES.
I NEED TO INSTALL
A WHOLE NEW OPERATING SYSTEM
TO STEER THIS THING
OUT OF THE CITY.
BUT YOU'RE LUKE.
THERE'S ALWAYS SOME
SUPERGENIUS GIGABYTE-FILLED
RABBIT IN A HAT
SOMEWHERE, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
MY HELMET'S AI.
WHOA. OK.
IT CAN DO THAT?
WELL, MY DAD DESIGNED
THE BATTECH
TO TALK TO EACH OTHER.
THE AI IS THE ONLY THING
THAT COULD OVERRIDE
THIS NAV SYSTEM IN TIME.
IF I CAN DOCK IT
TO THE MAINFRAME,
WE MIGHT ACTUALLY HAVE
A FIGHTING CHANCE.
WAIT. DOCK IT?
AS IN LEAVE IT BEHIND?
ONLY WAY THIS WORKS.
BUT, LUKE, THAT'S
YOUR DAD.
SOPHIE... GIVE ME
A DIRECTION I CAN GET TO
IN 2 MINUTES
AND 15 SECONDS.
COPY. I'M ON IT.
- HUH!
- UNH!
HA HA HA!
DO BATS HAVE
9 LIVES, TOO?
BECAUSE I DON'T THINK YOU
CAN HOLD US UP MUCH LONGER.
YOU WILLING TO
KILL ME
OR DIE FOR ME, SIS?
NOT... LETTING GO.
IS IT JUST ME,
OR IS THIS EVIL PLAN
UNFOLDING EXACTLY
AS I CALLED IT?
LOOK AT ME DOING
SOMETHING OUT
OF THE GOODNESS
OF MY HEART.
I'M SURPRISED YOU DIDN'T
SPONTANEOUSLY BURST INTO FLAMES.
IT MUST MEAN I'VE
REALLY CHANGED.
DID THIS EARN ME
THE BUZZER OR WHAT?
YOU REALLY WILLING
TO DITCH THE BITCH?
I WATCHED MY MOM'S
HEAD
BOBBING DOWN A RIVER,
ENDURED A LIFE SENTENCE
IN A MONSTER'S BASEMENT
AND HAD MY HEAD
SCRAMBLED
BY A WOMAN SCORNED.
NOW I'M COMING
TO YOU OF ALL PEOPLE
FOR SOME MAGIC KEY TO
MAKE THE CRAZY GO POOF.
THAT MUST SHOW YOU
HOW DESPERATE I AM.
I DON'T SEE DESPERATE.
I SEE A GIRL
WHO LIVED
A HELL OF A LIFE
CAPABLE OF CHANGE.
I CAN'T... DO IT
ON MY OWN!
NO. YOU DON'T WANT TO
DO IT ON YOUR OWN
BECAUSE IT'S HARD,
BUT IF ANYONE CAN SURVIVE
HARD, ALICE, IT'S YOU.
THIS... IS FOR MARY,
BUT DEEP DOWN,
MARY KNOWS
AND I KNOW AND YOU KNOW
YOU ARE NOT THE ONE
WHO NEEDS THIS.
♪ ANYWHERE YOU GO
UGH.
♪ I FOLLOW
AAH! ERR!
THANK YOU.
I MEAN IT.
TO BE CLEAR...
WE STILL AREN'T
FRIENDS,
AND I CAN'T HELP
YOU WITH THAT.
LESS THAN
A MINUTE, BATWING.
HOW MUCH LONGER
BEFORE IT'S OPERATIONAL?
AI's IN.
JUST NEED COORDINATES.
SOPHIE, NOW.
THESE CALCULATIONS
WERE MADE WHEN WE
STILL HAD TWO MINUTES
ON THE CLOCK.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WE DON'T HAVE TIME
TO GET IT OUT
OF GOTHAM?
BATCAVE,
I NEED A DIRECTION ASAP!
20 SECONDS.
SOPHIE! COORDINATES!
OK. UM,
40 DEGREES NORTH,
73 DEGREES WEST.
IF WE CAN'T GET IT
TO THE OCEAN,
WE CAN AT LEAST GET
IT TO THE CITY'S
MOST DESOLATE AREA.
IT'S WORKING.
NOW GET OUT OF THERE.
YOU INSPIRED ME
TO BE A HERO.
THANKS, DAD.
I'M PROUD
OF YOU, SON.
YOU AND YOUR TEAM WILL SAVE
A LOT OF LIVES TONIGHT.
NOW GO SAVE YOURS.
BATCAVE TO BATWING,
DO YOU READ?
BATWING, CHECK IN.
ARE YOU OK?
I'M HERE.
I GOT OUT OF THERE.
- HELLO?
- HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING OUT HERE?
GOT SPLIT UP
FROM MY MOM.
I DON'T KNOW
WHERE SHE WENT.
OK. I'll HELP YOU
FIND HER.
WHO ARE YOU ANYWAY?
CALL ME BATWING.
HOW IS HE?
HIS VITALS
ARE STABLE.
PHYSICALLY,
HE'S OK,
BUT UNTIL HE
WAKES UP,
WE WON'T KNOW IF
THE BUZZER WORKED.
IT'S GOING TO WORK.
♪ AH AH AH AH
AH AH AH AH ♪
THANK YOU FOR FINDING A
WAY TO MAKE THIS HAPPEN.
I TOLD YOU YOU COULD
TRUST ME.
RYAN... DESPITE
MY MISTAKES,
YOU HAVE EXCEEDED
MY WILDEST DREAMS.
I CAN'T CHANGE
THE PAST,
BUT MAYBE WE CAN BUILD
A DIFFERENT FUTURE.
♪ THINGS ARE LOOKING
UP NOW, BABY ♪
I'D LIKE THAT.
♪ EVEN WHEN
THE WORLD IS SPINNING... ♪
MARQUIS?
BABY, CAN YOU
HEAR ME?
♪ AND EVEN THOUGH
I KNOW WE'RE FIGHTING ♪
♪ HOLDING ON,
AND JUST SURVIVING ♪
HI, MOM.
♪ YOU MAKE IT BETTER,
BETTER, BETTER ♪
♪ BETTER THAN THIS
HEY, SIS.
NICE TO MEET YOU
FOR REAL.
♪ YOU MAKE IT BETTER
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
♪ AND LIFE IS A MESS
♪ ALL OF US ARE JUST
TRYING TO MAKE IT ♪
LIKE I NEED
MY LITTLE SISTER.
♪ WE GET SO DEPRESSED
♪ REACH ALL OUR LIMITS
♪ BUT I LOVE YOU,
AND THERE'S NO MISTAKING ♪
♪ THAT YOU MAKE IT
BETTER, BETTER, BETTER ♪
SERIOUSLY?
♪ BETTER THAN THAT
♪ BETTER, BETTER, BETTER
♪ YOU MAKE IT BETTER
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THE BEST
♪ SMILE ON ME
GOOD FOR YOU, BETH.
♪ YOU BEAUTIFUL SOUL
♪ SMILE ON, BABY
♪ GO ON
♪ THE LIGHT YOU SHINE
♪ DESERVES TO SHOW
♪ HOW FAR YOU'VE COME
SO WHAT NEXT?
WELL, NOW THAT WE'VE
GOT WAYNE BACK,
WHAT'S NEXT IS RECLAIMING
THIS SPACE
AS IN WHAT IS UP
WITH TACKY-ASS TV
COVERING
MY STAINED GLASS?
I MEAN... WHAT'S
NEXT FOR US?
WELL, I THOUGHT WE AGREED
YOU WERE GONNA BUY ME DINNER.
♪ YOU MAKE IT
BETTER, BETTER, BETTER ♪
♪ BETTER THAN THIS
AND BETTER THAN THAT ♪
BROUGHT THE CHAMPS!
AND WE'RE
INTERRUPTING.
THIS IS GONNA KEEP
HAPPENING, ISN'T IT?
- PROBABLY.
WELL, I FOR ONE
AM NOT GONNA LET
A SLIGHTLY AWKWARD
SENSATION GET IN THE WAY
OF OUR RARE
OPPORTUNITY
TO CELEBRATE!
I'M ACTUALLY GLAD
YOU'RE ALL HERE.
I NEED YOUR HELP
GETTING THIS PLACE
RIGHT AGAIN.
STARTING WITH THIS.
♪ BETTER, BETTER, BETTER
THAT'S BETTER.
SO DO I WANT TO KNOW WHAT
HE DID TO OUR BATCAVE?
DOESN'T BATWOMAN
TAKE A NIGHT OFF?
THIS IS GOTHAM, HOME
OF THE INFECTIOUS REPTILE TEETH,
DUDES IN PIG MASKS,
A KILLER VINE CAUSING
MY BESTIE TO GET HER BADDIE ON.
IF I HAVE LEARNED ANYTHING,
IT IS TO BE PREPARED
FOR EVERYTHING AT ALL TIMES.
ARE Y'ALL WITH ME?
WE'RE WITH YOU,
BATWOMAN.
WHERE ELSE
WOULD WE BE?
YEAH. OH. I THOUGHT
WE WERE DRINKING.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M JUST...
I'll TAKE IT WITH.
LET'S GET TO WORK.
THIS IS DANA DEWITT LIVE
FROM THE TOXIC SCENE
THAT COULD'VE DESTROYED
GOTHAM CITY
WITHOUT THE HEROICS
OF BATWOMAN.
THE CITY HAS ADVISED CITIZENS
TO STAY AWAY FROM THE AREA
AS THEY ASSESS THE HAZARDOUS
AIR QUALITY CAUSED
BY THE JOKER'S ACID BOMB
THAT BLANKETED THE NEIGHBOR...
OH, MY GOD. WHAT IS THAT?
AAH! OH, MY GOD!
GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD!