Last season on Batwoman...
New look.
New Batwoman.
What is this place?
It was where Bruce kept the weapons
he confiscated from all
the villains he took down.
When I was a kid, I drew pictures
of how I imagined
a Black Batman would look.
Turns out my dad was secretly turning
those pictures into reality.
Your mother didn't die
in childbirth, Ry-Ry.
Mommy dearest...
is still very much alive.
So what's next, Batwoman?
We're gonna find that
case of Batman trophies
before anyone else does.
_
It didn't take long
for the psychiatric unit
at Gotham University hospital to make
the recommendation to the courts.
Wonderland Gang leader Alice,
AKA the missing
and presumed dead Beth Kane,
will not stand trial
but instead will continue her residency
at Arkham Asylum
for the criminally insane.
Curiouser and curiouser.
I will show them
exactly how wrong they are about you,
and I will have so much fun doing it.
Heh.
Just as you would want,
my dear, sweet Alice.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
- Raah!
- Unh!
Where were we? Oh, yeah. Sidekick names.
Just FYI, no sidekick actually likes
being referred to as a sidekick.
Copy that, my number two dude.
Nope, not that either.
"All the more reason
for me to find a way
to get you out of there".
"I promise you I'm not
giving up on you this time.
More to come"...
"Your father".
Kane... Visitor.
So I have an idea for a name.
Just please don't say Black Batman.
Seriously? Black Batman?
Coming from the girl
who inherited her code name.
You know what? I got one.
The Dork Knight. Ha!
Just look for the damn Poison Ivy.
Hey. Are you sure they shipped it here?
Believe it or not,
Poison Ivy doesn't get
a lot of action on the dark web,
so I got creative, honed in on people
who could actually
benefit from a mystical,
fast-growing vine, found these guys
looking for a way to expand
their marijuana crop.
The shipment was supposed
to come in today.
Of all the artifacts
that fell into the river,
a Poison Ivy sprig doesn't
exactly scream moneymaker.
Bingo.
Hey. Is it just me,
or has this quadrupled
since Circe took it?
Someone just probably got it wet.
Keep it away from the light.
_
Aah!
Hey! You copy?
What the hell was that?
So, what, we're, uh, sisters now?
Far from it.
I graduate med school tomorrow,
and Dad's one wish was
for me to check on you
and keep you from going
off the deep end,
so this is me pretending to care
so I don't have to lie
to him when he calls me
tomorrow to congratulate me.
That is so sweet...
- Mmm.
- But I'm good.
I can smell you through this partition,
so I beg to differ.
See, that's the thing.
None of this matters
because Daddy's gonna find a way
to get me out of here.
Really? From the top bunk of his cell
in Metropolis?
Even incarcerated, Daddy's one
of the most connected men
in Gotham City.
What makes you believe that?
Oh, he didn't tell you?
Yeah. We've been, um, writing,
so I know you came to make
sure that I was miserable,
but I'm sorry to inform you I'm not.
Fine. Then this is me punching in
and promptly punching out.
See you, Alice.
One quick question while I have you.
It's about your little pal Ryan.
4 down, how many still out there?
A lot.
But at least in the meantime,
we prevented Gotham from
a cortisone shortage.
So you want to tell me
why you froze up back there?
I didn't freeze up. The suit did.
It just glitches out sometimes.
Because I can't be watching
both of our asses.
Yeah, I know that, and I'll fix it.
Graduation tickets. I go on at 7:00,
which means your butt
needs to be in your seat
at 6:30 sharp!
So if there's a bomber
threatening to take out
half the city, just remember that
I only become an official MD once,
and people bomb Gotham every other day.
Now if you'll excuse me, I have to go
shower off my encounter with Alice.
Apparently, she and my dad
are pen pals now.
That's... uncomfortable.
I've barely even heard from
him since he was put away,
but sure, reconnect with the chick
who killed your second wife.
I'll just be graduating tomorrow.
You know, valedictorian,
top of my class,
but as long as Alice knows
that you're thinking of her...
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I know your family
can't be there tomorrow,
but this family can,
and we won't miss it.
Yeah. Oh. That reminds me.
Alice told me to ask you
about your birth mom.
- Huh?
- She was like,
"Ryan will know what I mean",
and then she smiled like a total creep.
Your mom died in childbirth.
That's dark even for Alice.
So you don't know
what she's referring to?
Since when does Alice ever make sense?
I can relate to Alice
on a deeply personal level,
which is why I am here
at her last known hideout,
where society shoved her
back into the sewers.
At the tender age of 13,
she was lost, forgotten,
held captive, tortured!
Who wouldn't break under all that?
Locking her away in Arkham
is just victimizing her
all over again!
You know you drank too much
when you're seeing leprechauns.
Free Alice? That woman
is a full-blown lunatic.
Alice is a survivor.
Pay her some respect.
Alice is just another victim
of a flawed bureaucratic system.
She deserves her day in court.
Dude, why did... why did you say that?
Heh. Heh heh.
No idea why I just said that. Ha ha ha!
Yeah. What the hell was that?
What's happening with your hat, huh?
Let go of me!
Curiouser and curiouser.
What the hell's going on?
Uh, let's just get out of here, dude.
Stand still.
Why can't I move?
Kill him.
I'm not killing my friend, freak.
Dude, what are you doing?
No, no. What are you doing?
What are you doing? Aah!
What the hell was that?
What did you make me do, you psycho?
You're a fricking psycho!
Mad as a hatter. Ha ha ha!
_
Yo. Hey. I have something for you.
I'm sleeping. Go away.
I think you're gonna want to see this.
Isn't that the Batman guy,
the Mad Hatter?
I remember him from when I was a kid.
_
Move.
I swear I would... I would
never kill anyone.
It was like one second
I'm... I'm laughing
at some... some loser dressed up,
and the next thing I know, I'm...
slicing open my buddy's throat.
It was completely out of my control.
What makes you think
it was the Mad Hatter?
Oh, Montoya. Last I checked,
you traded that big, shiny pin
for a basement desk in the City Hall.
What's it again, freak squad?
The Rogues Unit.
Was he short, old, what?
Nah. Younger.
Lanky, dork-like.
He's a Mad Hatter imposter,
which means he found the hat.
No, no. What are you doing?
No! No, no, no!
What... what the hell did you just do?
I don't know what's
more disturbing... that,
that he posted it, or that Alice
actually has a fanboy.
Sorry. How does a top hat make someone
kill their drinking buddy?
Right. Meet Jervis Tetch,
AKA the original Mad Hatter.
Now according to my dad,
Jervis Tetch was a tiny, insecure,
and annoying neuroscientist.
He felt like the world
wasn't listening to him,
so he developed mind control technology
to force them to listen.
He built it directly into his hat.
Okay. This says Bruce had
the hat deprogrammed
before he put it into the trophy case.
My guess is that the technology latches
to the brain activity of the
first person who puts it on.
If the hat is technology, can't we
hack it or whatever?
It's not exactly uploaded to the cloud.
We first need to get
the hat off his head.
Well, how without falling
victim to it in the process?
128 hertz of frequency.
Your dad figured out how to disrupt
the hat's radio waves.
Okay. So we know the how and the what.
We just need to know the where.
So if I were an Alice-obsessed
Mad Hatter wannabe, where would I go?
I was wondering when
you'd come crawling back.
You stormed out of here
in such a... huff last time,
I was worried it was something I said.
Tell me what you're planning
with your Mad Hatter superfan.
I told you I don't know him.
Well, he certainly knows
a lot about you.
Have you watched the news?
My identity's been outed,
and some people actually appreciate
that I'm just a girl standing in front
of a psychiatric ward,
asking them not to
fry her brain.
- Uh-huh.
- Oh, come on.
We both know I'm utterly
helpless behind these walls.
You came because you want
all the dirty deets on Mommy D.
I saw my birth mother's
death certificate.
Nia A. Wilder. died the day I was born.
If you say so, dear.
What is this? Hmm?
Are you lonely?
You need to keep somebody
on a leash to stop you from slipping
into total isolation?
Heh heh heh.
Am I lonely?
Look at your life.
Your closest emotional connection
is an ex in witness protection.
You have no one.
I gave you someone to fill the hole
in your little, empty heart.
I have my friends.
Luke and Mary?
Right. Who you're so close to
you couldn't even tell your birth mother
lied to you all these years.
- We're done here.
- Sounds like your Mad Hatter's
planning a tea party.
Do you know what he's planning, Alice?
I just know what I would do.
Which is?
It would be so refreshing
if a supervillain actually said
what they meant for once.
What tea party?
Not to kill the mood,
but the last tea party Alice had,
she poisoned your mom.
So what, he's making
it personal, more public?
You know what? I should ask my dad.
Maybe he's chatted about it with Alice
in their correspondence.
Okay. You, my dear, are graduating
top of your class,
looking fine as hell might I add,
and we are standing
here talking about Alice.
Can we not let that bitch
ruin the best thing
we have going on right now, please?
Fine. Subject change.
Who's this Deja girl you ditched
me for last night, hmm?
I thought her name was Riley.
Oh, no. Riley was last week.
Um, excuse me. I'm allowed to date
multiple women at once.
So I take it you and Kate
are not happening?
Oh, no. They're good.
They're friends,
but it's too complicated
for anything more right now.
Thank you, Mary. Yes to all of that.
Ryan Wilder, I think
this is the most interest
you've ever shown my love life.
At least somebody's getting
some around here.
You know, the more I think
about this tea party thing,
if there's one person who can predict
a lunatic's next move, it's another
certifiable lunatic.
That's what I can't shake.
She has no reason to make this up.
She has every reason...
because this is all a game to her.
She's trying to feel relevant because
she doesn't matter anymore.
Now seriously, drop it
before y'all both kill my buzz.
Y'all know this wasn't a cheap-ass
bottle of champagne.
I'm gonna go check on her.
I should go practice my speech.
Want to tell me what happened at Arkham?
Nothing because Alice was unhelpful
and petulant and everything
one would expect Alice to be.
Then if she was everything you expected,
how'd she get under your skin?
Ryan, what happened?
She said my biological mother,
who died giving birth to me,
was actually still alive
and that she covered it
all up with a fake name
so I'd never find her.
- Damn.
- And as much as I don't believe
a word Alice says...
There's still a part
of you that can't help
but wonder "Is my mom still alive?"
I take it Mary and Luke don't know.
I don't know if I want to know.
I was told my whole life that my dad
was out of the picture and
my mom died in the hospital.
What if I have a family out there?
Want me to look into it on the DL?
Thank you.
Testing 1, 2, 3.
Hey. You're not supposed to be up here.
I got a guy matching the
top hat loony from the news.
I'm just testing the microphone,
making sure that my voice projects
all the way to the back.
Perfect. You're all here.
Gather around, friends.
It's a lovely afternoon...
for tea.
Gotham City Vital Records.
Hi. I was hoping you could
e-mail me a birth certificate.
Mail only. 4-6 weeks.
Okay. Thanks anyway.
I'll just hack into your system
and find it myself.
Let's see. Who was
the attending physician?
Dr. Quadracci.
Shady doctor. Here we go.
Mayor Hartley.
See this sandwich, Montoya?
I haven't eaten since 9:30.
The Mad Hatter's a copycat.
I think he's somehow gotten ahold
of the original hat,
which doesn't make sense
because Batman took it off the streets
and locked it down 20 years ago.
Am I special, or did you
torture Mayor Akins, too?
He hired me, ma'am,
to run the Rogues Unit.
I convinced him it's
only a matter of time
before Batman's enemies come
crawling out of the sewer
looking for their toys, and here we are.
And it's not just the Mad Hatter's hat.
Of course it's not.
Apparently, a cutting of Poison Ivy
was bouncing around the dark web
for the past 3 days.
If someone's leaking
these back onto the streets,
I need to see what else is out there.
Look. I am 30 days
into this whole Mayor gig,
and I am not putting the
words "rogues" or "toys"
onto my budget.
What about the words "mass casualty"
and "preventable" on
your resignation letter?
Mayor, I love this city in my bones,
and I need you to hear
me before this becomes
Jim Gordon's Gotham all over again.
It's a two-drink limit, so sip slowly.
Okay. What?
Alice was right.
Nia A. Wilder doesn't exist.
I saw her death certificate.
The doctor who signed
her death certificate
also signed your birth certificate.
Two months later, he lost his license
for an unrelated wire fraud,
so I honed in on him.
He had 25 patients in the days
surrounding your birth.
I looked into all of them,
and one came into the hospital
a day before you were born,
according to her medical files,
she was suffering
from a cyst on her ovary,
so I followed the money.
She paid him $2 million
after her so-called emergency surgery.
$2 million to cover up her
pregnancy with me? Why?
I have no idea,
but your mom's still alive, Ryan.
And my dad?
Nothing. Just her.
Here.
If you want to know her name,
and if you don't, I get that, too.
Two-drink limit?
What are we talking about?
Let's find our seats.
Okay. Smile.
Okay. Say, "Cheese!" Ha ha!
Aah!
Ready for your big speech?
Dr. Hall, sorry. I was
just having a moment.
I'm sure your family would be proud.
They'd better be.
You're one of the best students
that's ever come through this school.
Thank you, Dr. Hall.
Dr. Hamilton,
you are the spitting
image of your mother.
Do no harm.
Today, we take the hippocratic oath...
But shouldn't it be called
the hypocrite oath?
I mean, doctors are supposed to uphold
the highest ethical
medical standards, right?
Instead, it's "How many patients
can I see in a day?
And "Sorry. We don't
take that insurance"
and "That bandage costs $300".
What happened to the Gotham
medical community?
- Did she change her speech?
- This is not her speech.
Don't even get me started
on mental health care.
Do you know the process
of institutionalizing someone?
It took our Alma mater Gotham U
under the oversight
of our chair Dr. Hall...
a measly 10 minutes to decide
that Alice would be an Arkham lifer.
So what, we just give up on her?
This is not Mary talking.
He got to her. He's here.
What about the fact that
she was victimized
for over a decade,
that her own family gave up on her,
that she was replaced...
by me?
This is what Alice meant.
This is his tea party.
If you have ear buds, put them on.
I'm texting you a disruptor frequency
to block his mind control.
No!
Everybody shut up
and take your seats until
I instruct you otherwise.
The show is about to begin.
Now if you are going
to wield the power of a god,
prove you are worthy.
Remove this man's organs one at a time
until he dies.
You need help.
You sound like all my doctors.
Okay. We need to take him out.
No, no. We can't do that.
He's already brain-jacked everyone here.
We need to get him to reverse
it before Mary kills that guy.
How? Ask nicely?
There is one person he'll listen to.
- No.
- Ryan,
Mary's about to de-organ
the chair of her university.
Absolutely not.
Okay. What am I missing?
We can get Liam to
undo the mind control,
but we have to break
Alice out of Arkham first.
It may have taken him 15 years
and several dead wives,
but daddy finally understands
that I'm still his little girl,
and he is going to use
every last resource
that he has left to get
me out of this hell hole
and as far away from Gotham as possible.
Alice, we've been over this.
Your father is incarcerated himself.
No one is coming to rescue you.
Unh!
Oh, okay. Everyone stay calm.
Daddy?
What? No.
Alice, we're going. Let's go.
- Get off of me!
- I need you to come with me!
Help, help! Help! Help me!
I see she's found the appendix.
Starting with the unnecessary
organs first,
prolonging the inevitable.
Appendix is out. Luke, where are you?
Headed to the roof as we speak.
I can't stop any of Liam's
previous commands.
Only he can do that,
but this should protect
everyone from any of
his future commands.
Get ready to rock.
What are you doing?
Put your phones away.
Stop!
Alice, I need you!
Mary needs you! Open this damn door!
My dad is gonna take me
away from Gotham,
from all of you!
- Leave me alone!
- Your dad's not coming, Alice!
He is. He told me.
He... he promised in...
in his postcards.
He... he promised.
- What, these?
- Yeah.
This is an ad from a magazine, Alice.
It's for soap.
This is a page from
the Arkham directory,
a napkin from the cafeteria.
This is a coloring book page!
- What?
- Your dad is not writing to you.
He sent me these.
I read them with my own eyes.
Your mind is playing tricks on you.
Look. I get it.
You lost Ocean, your dad, Kate.
Now you're back in here. It's too much.
He's coming because he
promised me he's coming.
It's garbage, Alice!
Help us.
If you help us,
you can run,
and I won't stop you.
Ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
I'm sure that was a lot.
You want to talk about it?
There's no point.
Did you say something? Alice?
Alice, did you say something?
Well, I can't exactly meet
my future boyfriend
in this, can I?
Mary.
I'm here. What do we do?
How do we save him?
We can't.
I took his appendix, his gallbladder,
a kidney, his spleen.
I'm down to vitals.
I have to keep removing his organs
until he dies.
- Then kill him.
- What?
Kill him. He's got no chance
if you remove anything else.
We shock his heart,
he goes into cardiac arrest
and dies just like
the Mad Hatter guy wanted.
It'll break his mind control.
But then what?
Then we pray like hell you can bring
Dr. Hall back to life.
Graduates wearing those
pretentious stethoscopes,
make them useful.
Tie them around your throats!
Unh!
Hyah! Unh!
What the hell happened?
The damn suit fritzed out again.
Okay. No pulse. He's dead.
How do you feel?
Like I have my own brain back.
It worked. I broke his control.
Good. Hopefully, this does, too.
Okay.
Charge.
Clear.
Such wasted potential.
Ah, the old strangle
yourself to death gag.
It's a classic.
You're supposed to be in Arkham.
Well, I had to meet my number one fan.
Heh heh. What did I miss?
Do you remember when you
forced Catherine Hamilton
to reveal what a garbage human she is
in front of all her peers?
- Mm-hmm.
- I just did the same thing
to her daughter.
- Clever boy.
- It's true.
Doctors are all the same.
They think they're gods amongst men.
Why should I be institutionalized?
Because you think I'm crazy?
Because I see the world
a little differently than you?
Sorry for being my own person!
Heh heh. I heard you filmed yourself
throwing a kitten off a rooftop.
- You heard about that.
- Mmm. Yeah.
Did you see it? 5,070 views.
Heh heh.
Tell all these people to stop.
Alice... they have too much power.
Think about it.
All they have to do is
sign a piece of paper,
and surprise, you're bankrupt!
Surprise, you're addicted to medication.
Surprise, you're labeled crazy
forever and ever.
I'm not crazy, Alice!
If any of these people die,
they will have a reason
to lock you away forever.
Do you think I'm crazy?
The truth.
No...
I don't think you're crazy.
If it wasn't for you, guys like me
wouldn't have heroes.
Stop killing yourselves.
Get out of here.
There. Did that... earn me a hug?
Heh. Yeah.
Ahem.
Frequency jammers.
You're as crazy as they come, dear.
Word of advice... don't
ever meet your heroes.
You really are the monster
they say you are.
That's me.
What the hell are you?
I didn't kill him. He's fine.
You didn't think I was
actually gonna let you go?
You two-faced bitch.
I saved all those people for you.
No. For you because in that warped mind
you somehow thought today
would undo the hundreds
of horrible things you've done.
Please. This is about payback
because you can't handle the truth.
Don't hate me because
your family might be
more screwed up than mine.
Get her out of here!
In conclusion, my fellow graduates,
I challenge each and every one of you
to wake up every morning
and ask yourself
"How can I end this day
better than how it started?"
With one more saved life,
one more cancer-free scan,
one more smile
because if we can do that every day,
together, we can leave this world
a better place than how we found it.
Whoo! A happy ending
to the worst commencement
ceremony in history.
Thanks. Look.
Today, was awful,
and Liam is obviously sick,
but he did make some good points
about the medical community
like for one maybe
we should stop referring
to troubled people as crazy lunatics.
Even Alice?
Heh. Even Alice.
Then I get to say something.
♪ Toast time ♪
Mary, you have probably
saved more people
than anyone in this city.
You are the person
that I go to for advice,
for a shoulder to cry on,
for... let's face it... pain meds.
You didn't need an MD
for the people who love you
to know that you are a true hero,
and it's really dope
we get to call you Dr. Hamilton.
- Hey!
- Congrats, roomie!
We are so proud of you.
- Love you, Mary.
- Cheers.
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
Okay. Not to bail early,
but I need to figure out
why my suit is crashing,
or Ryan will never let me
be her wingman again, so...
Wait a minute.
Wingman.
Bat... wing. Batwing.
Ooh. That's good.
I'll take that under consideration.
Good night.
Actually, can I show you
something downstairs?
Yeah, sure.
Okay. Cool.
Ahem. I'll just be, um...
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Everything is gonna be all right ♪
I'll keep the champagne cold.
Mary, Luke, the Bat...
that's my family.
I finally have everything I want.
Why risk losing it just to get to know
a woman who had no desire knowing me?
My opinion? Because
she's still your mom.
My whole life I wanted a family,
I wanted answers, I wanted
to belong to someone
and for someone to belong to me,
but that look on Liam's face today
when Alice wasn't
who he needed her to be,
it's not worth it.
I'm good.
Then consider it out of your life.
Yeah.
Dubai loved it.
Have the lawyers write up a contract
and get them a prototype
they can play with.
- Ma'am.
- Ohh.
Tell me you're not bringing me drama
before I've had my red wine.
Just got word of a security breach.
Then have the cyber team do their thing.
Why are you bothering me with it?
Because I don't think you'll want
the cyber team looking into it.
Somebody's been fishing
for very specific data,
not on the company, on you, ma'am.
Lucas Fox.
If you're hearing this message,
it means you found the suit.
Dad?
Dad, how am I hearing
your voice right now?
Because I'm your dad,
and I always know when you need me.
_
Never seen you before. You a cop?
Fortunately for you, no.
How do you have this list?
Over a dozen weapons of mass destruction
are belly up in the Gotham
river somewhere,
and your main concern is how I know?
I'm cleaning it up.
I'm sure that warms
the parents of the kid
whose buddy slit open
his throat the other night.
Where'd you get this list?
From me
in exchange for my freedom.
I don't know who you are,
but teaming up with Gotham's
most prolific criminal
is gonna blow up in your face.
It worked out well for you today.
You and Alice stopped a madman,
and he's just the beginning.
- Why did you call me here?
- You're strong,
and you have access.
She's got the mind of a psychopath,
so together, you two
are gonna find and stop
every freak who gets his hands
on one of these weapons
until each of the items
on that list are found
and accounted for.
Hard pass.
It's just as easy for me to shut down
your illegal vigilante operation...
Ryan Wilder.
- Heh.
- Wow!
All that time my boyfriend,
father, sister spent
trying to break through
to my good side...
tsk, tsk, tsk... silly them.
It's so much more fun on my bad side.
So do we have a deal or what?
Oh, yes. I for one am in.
Batwoman, answer the question.
You in,
or are you hanging up the cape?
Sounds like I don't have a choice.
Greg, move your head!
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -