PREVIOUSLY ON "BATWOMAN"...
MR. FREEZE'S
LIQUID NITROGEN CAN
GOT IN THE HANDS OF
A BUNCH OF EIGHTH GRADERS.
I NEED TO FIND IT.
EXPOSURE TO
THE FREEZE SERUM
WILL STOP TIME
AND KEEP YOU FROM AGING.
GONNA NEED
A LITTLE HELP.
BATWOMAN.
RYAN, WAKE UP!
NOT MUCH LEFT, BUT
RENEE WAS WILLING
TO CROSS IT OFF HER LIST.
GUESS IT'S SAFE TO
SAY YOU'VE FIGURED OUT
THE GLITCHES IN
YOUR SUPERSUIT.
YOU COULD SAY THAT.
IT'S BECAUSE HE
DISABLED THE FAILSAFE.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE CLEARED
YOU FOR FIELD DUTY.
IF YOU CONTINUE
TO TRY TO HAVE
ANYTHING TO DO
WITH MY FAMILY,
YOU AND WAYNE ENTERPRISES
WILL COME TO SEVERELY
REGRET THAT DECISION.
DOES THAT HAPPEN A LOT?
THOSE DELUSIONS?
SO, YOU THINK
YOU KNOW MY STORY.
27. RAISED IN THE SYSTEM.
STINT AT BLACKGATE.
OH, AND YOU'RE MY SISTER.
AAH!
SUBJECT FXJ-1.
REANIMATION PROGRESS CHECK.
FINAL PHASE.
YOU'RE FREE TO GO.
REANIMATION FAILURE.
24 HOURS TILL CLIENT DEADLINE.
WHAT THE HELL?
WHEN DID IT GET HERE?
TRAGICALLY EARLY.
DELIVERY DUDE
WOKE ME OUT OF BED.
OK. YEAH.
THIS IS BAD.
YEAH, BUT THE PICTURE'S
KIND OF CUTE.
"30 UNDER 30."
YOURS TRULY.
I MEAN, I NEED
TO HANG THIS UP.
- GIVE ME THE NOTE.
- HERE.
"YOU'RE WELCOME, FAM.
SEE YOU AT THE
PRESS JUNKET. MARQUIS."
YOUR BROTHER
GOT YOU ON THE LIST?
FIRST OF ALL,
I'M A RISING STAR.
BUT ALSO, HE USED
TO HOOK UP
WITH THE EDITOR OF
THE "GAZETTE," SO...
SO, YOU NOW HAVE
A PUBLIC DATE
IN FRONT OF THE CAMERAS
WITH THE BROTHER
THAT YOU HAVE TO
STAY AWAY FROM,
OTHERWISE JADA JET
COMES KNIVES OUT
FOR YOU, WAYNE ENTERPRISES,
MAYBE EVEN YOUR
SECRET IDENTITY.
I TRIED TO GHOST HIM, OK,
BUT THE WORD IS OUT
AND GOTHAM'S CURIOUS.
YOU KNOW
CHARLIE CLARKE, RIGHT?
HEAD OF PR FOR WAYNE?
OF COURSE.
CHARLIE'S BEEN AT WAYNE
SINCE MY DAD
WAS STILL THERE.
HE'S ONE OF BRUCE'S
INNER CIRCLE GUYS.
OK, WELL, CHARLIE'S GOTTEN
DOZENS OF REQUESTS
TO INTERVIEW WAYNE'S
HOT, YOUNG CEO...
THEIR WORDS, NOT MINE...
AND HE SAYS THAT IF
I SKIP OUT ON THIS EVENT,
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
REPORTERS TRYING TO CLIMB
THE WALLS OF WAYNE TOWER
TO GET ANSWERS.
OK. WHAT'S YOUR
PLAN FOR WHEN
YOU RUN INTO MARQUIS?
FEEL THIS SHOULDER.
COME ON. FEEL IT. FEEL IT.
- COLD AS THEY COME
- OK.
LOOK, IF I NEED
A CONVO BLOCKER,
SOPHIE'S GONNA BE THERE.
HER SIS IS ON THE LIST
FOR THE COMMUNITY CENTER.
OH. THAT IS
LEGITIMATELY COOL.
GREAT. YOU BOTH
ARE HERE.
CAN I RUN SOMETHING
CRAZY BY YOU?
MY SWEET GIRL.
DID YOU GO HOME
WITH A BOY LAST NIGHT?
NO. SEE,
THAT'S THE THING.
I'M PRETTY SURE
I SPENT THE NIGHT
ASLEEP ON A BENCH
IN THE MIDDLE OF
GOTHAM PARK.
WHOO. SO,
BUSY MORNING.
I SHOULD JET.
PUN INTENDED.
GOOD LUCK.
WOULD LUKE STILL
BE THIS UPSET
IF NOTHING WAS
ACTUALLY WRONG?
LUKE IS JUST FRUSTRATED.
YOU TOLD ME HIS PTSD
MADE HIM A RISK
IN THE FIELD.
HE JUST WANTS US
TO BE ABLE TO
KNOW WE CAN DEPEND ON HIM.
DEPEND ON HIM?
YOU MEAN LIKE
WHEN YOU WALK INTO
A ROOM AND SAY,
"HEY, SOMETHING
REALLY WEIRD
JUST HAPPENED TO ME.
CAN WE TALK ABOUT IT?"
HE'LL COME AROUND, OK?
BUT I'M HERE TO LISTEN.
I HAVE A JAM-PACKED DAY,
SO, CAN WE WALK AND TALK?
THEN WE SHOULD
JUST TABLE MY DRAMA,
BECAUSE I SORT OF NEED
AN ACTIVE LISTENER HERE.
OK. HOW ABOUT THIS?
I'LL BUY DRINKS
FOR HAPPY HOUR.
THEN YOU CAN UNLOAD?
SURE. I'LL JUST
JOURNAL UNTIL THEN.
BREATHE. JUST BREATHE.
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU'RE IN THE
NORMAN BATES OF PSYCH WARDS,
WITH A BILLION
NON-CONSENSUAL NANOBOTS
SWIMMING THROUGH
YOUR BLOODSTREAM.
OH, WAIT.
YOU'VE GOT MAIL.
I HATE THAT I'M OLD ENOUGH
TO KNOW WHAT YOU DID THERE.
THESE ARE FROM DADDY.
THEY ALL ARE.
AN ENTIRE STACK
FROM OLE JAILCROW
JACOB KANE.
THESE MIS-DELIVERIES
ARE FROM
THE WEEPY POST OFFICE
INSIDE MY SICK MIND.
NOW, THAT SOUNDS LIKE
A "YOU" PROBLEM.
OOH!
EXCUSE ME?
HELP?
KANE?
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
EVERYTHING LOOKS
NORMAL TO YOU?
ROOM INSPECTIONS ARE
TUESDAYS AND THURSDAYS.
- WHAT?
- I HAVE JUST ONE MORE THING.
I NEED TO SPEAK
TO RENEE MONTOYA.
LET'S KEEP THINGS
MOVING, CHARLIE.
I WANT TO MAKE
AN IMPRESSION,
THEN LEAVE 'EM
WANTING MORE.
GREAT NEWS... THE CHAIRMAN
OF APEX BROADCASTING
GOT AN EEL BONE
STUCK IN HIS THROAT,
SO, THERE'S A PHOTO SESSION
SLOT AVAILABLE.
LEAD THE WAY.
WAYNE ENTERPRISES
IS SET TO MAKE
ITS BIGGEST QUARTERLY
REVENUE GAINS
IN 6 YEARS.
I HAD TO BRIBE MR. WAYNE
WITH BLOODY MARYS
TO GET HIM TO MEMORIZE
HIS TALKING POINTS.
RYAN! RYAN! RYAN!
OVER HERE.
YOU WANT TO
LET ME WORK?
I CAN BARELY TELL
YOU'RE SMILING.
COME ON!
SHOW GOTHAM
THAT NEW FIRE
THAT'S TAKING OVER.
RYAN, RYAN.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
ISN'T SHE WONDERFUL, FOLKS?
THAT'S MARQUIS JET.
I WANT THE CAMERAS
TO GET A SHOT
OF YOU TOGETHER.
THE JETS ARE
ICONS IN THIS CITY.
WHY ARE YOU
AVOIDING ME?
I THOUGHT THAT ONCE I
GOT YOU ON THIS LIST,
YOU KNEW THAT
I WANTED...
TO PISS OFF YOUR MOM.
HEY, I'M JUST MAKING UP
FOR THE MISSED TIME
YOU HAD WITH
OUR MOM IN
THE REBELLIOUS PHASE.
IT'S MANIPULATIVE.
AND FRANKLY,
IT PUTS MY BUSINESS
AT RISK.
- LOOK, RYAN...
- HEY, GUYS.
CAN I GET A SMILE?
I'LL BE
REAL WITH YOU.
I JUST WANTED TO DO
A NICE THING
AND HOPEFULLY
HAVE A CHANCE
TO HANG OUT WITH
MY SISTER, BUT
IF THAT'S TOO
RISKY FOR YOU...
YOU'RE OFF THE HOOK.
I GOTTA TAKE THIS.
YEAH.
THIS IS LIKE
THE PUBLICIST
HUNGER GAMES.
DID YOU SEE THE SIGN
AT THE BAR
THAT SAYS,
"THE FREE CHAMPAGNE
IS FOR NOMINEES ONLY"?
YOU WANT ME
TO GET YOU A GLASS,
YOU SHOULD'VE BOUGHT ME
THAT BOX OF WINE
I WANTED IN COLLEGE.
OK, AS YOUR BIG SISTER,
I STAND BEHIND
THAT DECISION.
IT'S AS ON BRAND
FOR ME AS BEING
HERE TODAY IS
OFF BRAND FOR YOU.
AS AN HONOREE,
I GET A LITTLE
SPEECH AT
THE PARTY LATER.
TWO MINUTES,
ANYTHING I WANT TO SAY.
MY PLAN IS TO SERENADE
THESE MONEYBAGS INTO
QUADRUPLING THE COMMUNITY
CENTER'S BUDGET.
IT'S A ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME
SHOT, RIGHT?
THAT'S MY
"UNDER 30" BESTIE.
ALWAYS GOT HER EYE
ON THE PRIZE, AND, UM...
IT MUST RUN
IN THE FAMILY.
UM, I HAVE SOMETHING
EMBARRASSING TO
TELL YOU.
I AM SO IN.
I HAD A DREAM
ABOUT RYAN.
- OK.
- I WAS IN BED.
- AND I MUST HAVE BEEN SICK, BECAUSE
SHE BROUGHT ME
SOME SOUP.
WHAT KIND OF SOUP?
I WOKE UP BEFORE I
COULD EVEN TRY IT.
WHAT?
YOU WOKE UP EARLY.
IT'S A CLASSIC DREAM
ABOUT LONGING.
I KNEW YOU
REALLY LIKED HER.
WHY DID I TELL YOU THIS?
JORDAN, IT WASN'T A SEXUAL DREAM.
AT ALL.
DID RYAN BRING
A FLOWER WITH THE SOUP?
TOLD YA.
HEY. I'M 31,
I HAVE NO CAREER,
AND I AM SURROUNDED
BY ALL YOU
SICK, LITTLE PRODIGIES,
AND MY BRAIN
IS BEGGING ME,
"HEY, LOSER,
CAN YOU AT LEAST
FIND A GIRLFRIEND?"
BUT... THAT DOESN'T MEAN
IT HAS TO BE RYAN.
OR, AND HEAR ME OUT
ON THIS,
RYAN WILDER IS
HOT AS HELL,
AND YOU'RE
AMAZING TOGETHER.
YOU'RE STARING AGAIN.
I JUST...
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I HAVE TO GO.
- I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
- TO THE BATHROOM?
WORRY ABOUT
YOUR SPEECH.
JORDAN MOORE.
I'M FROM THE "GAZETTE."
WE'RE READY TO SIT
FOR YOUR INTERVIEW.
O-OK, SURE. LET ME
JUST GRAB MY PUBLICIST.
THAT WON'T
BE NECESSARY.
VESPER FAIRCHILD IS HOLDING.
VESPER, IT'S JADA.
I HAPPENED TO GLANCE
AT LAST WEEK'S RATINGS.
OUCH. IT'S A CROWDED
LANDSCAPE, MY DEAR,
BUT I WANT TO HELP YOU
MAKE SOME NOISE.
YES, I HAVE A SCOOP.
EXPLAIN THIS NEW
HOBBY TO ME.
ONLY IF YOU EXPLAIN
WHY MONTOYA
DROPPED YOU OFF
FOR ME TO BABY-SIT.
I HAVE
URGENT INFORMATION
TO HELP BATWOMAN RECOVER
THE INFAMOUS
"ZERO-G" SNEAKERS
USED BY BATMAN'S
LONG-AGO FALLEN
AND TRAGICALLY
ARROGANT FOE
THE MIGHTY ICARUS.
ICARUS?
SOUNDS LIKE A DEEP CUT.
ACTUALLY,
IT'S FAKE, BUT
SHE'LL BELIEVE
ANYTHING IF YOU
LOWER YOUR VOICE
AN OCTAVE.
IT'S CONVINCING, RIGHT?
CONVINCE ME
NOT TO TELL MONTOYA THAT
THERE IS NO MIGHTY ICARUS.
WELL, FOR ONE,
YOU'RE LONELY.
I THOUGHT MAYBE WE COULD
DO EACH OTHER'S NAILS
OR TRY A FEW
ELECTIVE SURGERIES.
MM-HMM. THERE HAS TO
BE SOME REASON
WHY YOU'RE PLAYING
HOOKY FROM ARKHAM.
UHH. WELL, I HATE
TO ADMIT ANYTHING
THAT WOULD MAKE ME
SOUND WEAK,
BUT THE TRUTH IS...
I'M HERE TO DO
BATWOMAN A FAVOR.
MM. WELL, KEEP GOING.
SO FAR, THIS STORY'S
BETTER THAN
YOUR NANOBOT COLD.
FIRST THINGS FIRST.
CAN YOU TELL ME
WHAT TROPHY
THE BAT TEAM IS
HEROICALLY TRACKING DOWN
AT THIS VERY MOMENT
TO KEEP
THE GOTHAM STREETS SAFE
AND APPEASE
THE TYRANT THAT IS
FORCING US
TO WORK TOGETHER?
SOMETHING CAME UP.
WE'LL GET BACK TO
RENEE'S TREASURE HUNT TOMORROW.
HMM. NO JUDGMENT
HERE, BUT
I WONDER IF
RENEE WOULD BE AS
GENEROUS TOWARD
THIS WHOLE
WORK-LIFE BALANCE?
I GUESS YOU'LL FIND OUT
WHEN YOU CALL HER.
FINE. YOU WIN. JUST...
DON'T BOTHER ANYONE
WHO COMES IN.
THANK YOU.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'VE
NEVER HAD MEDIA TRAINING.
JUST HIGHLY MOTIVATED.
WHO'S NEXT?
LET ME SHOOT THE
"GAZETTE" A QUICK TEXT
AND SEE IF THEY'RE
READY FOR YOU.
FIGURED YOU'D CHILL IF
I BOUGHT A DISGUISE,
SO, THEY HAD THIS SICK
COLORWAY AT THE GIFT SHOP.
"WHO'S THAN MAN
WITH RYAN WILDER?
IS HE HANDSOME?
I CAN'T TELL."
YEAH, YOU PROBABLY
SHOULDA GOT SOME AVIATORS.
I SHOULD'VE.
THEY'RE TWO-FOR-ONE.
- DO YOU WANT IN?
HEY, RYAN,
HAVE YOU SEEN JORDAN?
SHE'S LATE FOR
AN INTERVIEW
AND HER PHONE IS OFF.
NEVER LET THE CLIENT
OUT OF YOUR SIGHT.
I'M MORE PUBLISISTER
THAN PUBLICIST, SO...
I'D HAVE GUESSED PRINT MODEL.
COOL HAT.
MARQUIS JET.
I'M RYAN'S BROTHER.
SOPHIE MOORE. RYAN'S...
VERY GOOD FRIEND
WHO NEEDS HELP
FINDING HER
BABY SISTER.
THE "GAZETTE"
SAYS THEY'RE READY FOR YOU.
CAN WE PUSH THIS OFF
UNTIL AFTER THE INTERVIEW?
MY GIRL COMES FIRST.
SEE IF THAT DUDE GOT
RID OF THE EEL BONE YET.
COME ON.
LET'S GO.
OK. REBOOTING...
VOICE INTERFACE.
REBOOTING SYSTEM LOADER.
DAD? IT'S LUKE.
ARE YOU THERE?
THE SILENT TREATMENT'S
GETTING OLD.
ARE YOU REALLY GONNA
LEAVE ME HANGING WITH THE MOST
SOPHISTICATED PERSONAL
FLIGHT SUIT ON THE PLANET?
IS THIS ABOUT
THE FAILSAFE?
YOU'RE MAD BECAUSE
I TURNED IT OFF?
BECAUSE THAT'S ON YOU.
IT MALFUNCTIONED. SO...
YOU KNOW, IT ALSO
ALMOST GOT ME KILLED,
SO, NO, I'M NOT
TURNING IT BACK ON.
MY SUIT, MY DECISION.
BATWOMAN TO BATCAVE.
YOU THERE?
YEAH, JUST...
TALKING TO MY WARDROBE.
HAVING A NORMAL ONE.
BATWOMAN. HEY.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
TAKING A PERSONAL DAY.
I NEED AN ASSIST.
SOPHIE'S SISTER JORDAN
IS M.I.A.
TOO MANY MAI TAIS
AT THE OPEN BAR?
OH, I HOPE NOT.
I CLEANED UP ENOUGH
PUKE IN MY OLD JOB.
I GOT A PING
ON HER CELL PHONE.
SO, LET ME JUST NARROW DOWN
THE LOCATION RADIUS
WITH THE HOTEL WI-FI.
NOT TO BE A DOWNER
AT A PARTY,
BUT IT MIGHT BE
TIME TO PANIC.
IS SOMETHING
GOING ON WITH HER?
SHE SEEMED NERVOUS
BUT ONLY BECAUSE
SHE HAD A SPEECH LATER.
FACIAL RECOGNITION
SAYS NO JORDAN
ON ANY OF THE EXTERIOR
HOTEL CAMS,
SO, SHE MUST STILL BE
ON THE PREMISES.
HEY, I JUST
GOT A TIP
THAT YOUR SISTER
WAS SPOTTED
UPSTAIRS
AT THE HOTEL.
SOME MAN BROUGHT HER
INTO ROOM 1620.
LET'S GO.
OK, YOU STAY HERE.
KEEP AN EYE OUT.
CALL ME IF SHE
COMES BACK DOWN.
JORDAN?
OH, MY GOD.
NO.
DON'T TOUCH HER.
NOT TILL WE KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED.
WHO THE HELL WOULD
DO THIS TO HER?
I'VE SEEN THIS
EQUIPMENT BEFORE.
THIS IS
MR. FREEZE'S DESIGN.
FREEZE SERUM
DID THIS?
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
YOU GOT THAT
STUFF OFF THE STREETS.
I GOT THE ORIGINAL
CANISTER BACK,
BUT MAYBE SOMEONE
FOUND MORE.
WHY WOULD THEY
DO THIS TO JORDAN?
AND HOW ARE THEY
DOING THIS
WITHOUT A CRYOCHAMBER?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'LL HANDLE IT.
- I HAVE TO MOVE HER.
- YOU CANNOT
WARM HER, SOPHIE.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS.
THE LAST TIME
SOMEONE TRIED THAT,
SHE AGED AT 4 TIMES
THE NORMAL RATE.
THIS IS MY SISTER, RYAN.
SHE'S MY RESPONSIBILITY.
I KNOW. WE WILL FIGURE
THIS OUT TOGETHER.
THE CATALYTIC MECHANISM IS
BASED ON
VICTOR FRIES' RESEARCH,
BUT WHAT USED TO HAPPEN
INSIDE A CHAMBER
IS NOW HAPPENING
INSIDE JORDAN'S CELLS.
I JUST WANT TO KNOW
HOW TO UNDO IT.
TELL ME HOW TO HELP.
THE MAIN
COMPLICATION THAT WE SEE
WITH FRIES' CRYO-STASIS
IS RAPID AGING,
BUT THIS IS SO MUCH
MORE INVASIVE.
IF I HAD TO GUESS
WHAT THIS COULD DO
TO ORGANIC TISSUE...
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN
A PIECE OF
PETRIFIED WOOD BEFORE?
WE SHOULD JUST PAUSE
ON THAT ANALOGY
AND JUST FOCUS.
WHAT DO YOU NEED?
WANT ME TO GO TO THE STORE
FOR A HAIR DRYER?
WHY THE HELL IS
ALICE EVEN HERE?
IT'S REALLY NOT EVEN
WORTH EXPLAINING.
LOOK, IF I CAN GET
A CLEAN SAMPLE
OF THIS NEW
FREEZE SERUM,
I THINK I COULD
FIGURE OUT
A SAFE WAY TO
BRING JORDAN OUT OF CRYO.
THEN WE SHOULD
FIND OUT WHO MADE IT
AND SEE IF
THEY HAVE MORE.
WERE THEY WORKING
WITH ANYONE
AT THE HOTEL OR
WITH THE EVENT?
WE SHOULD HAVE LUKE
CHECK EVERY CAMERA SYSTEM
TO SEE IF
HE CAN PULL...
I GOT IT.
IT'S THE BEE GEES.
OF COURSE IT'S THEM.
DID YOU TAKE
MY SISTER'S PHONE?
OH. YEAH.
AND, UM, YOU'RE WELCOME.
FOR CRITIQUING
HER STATE IN MUSIC?
NO. FOR SOLVING
ALL YOUR LITTLE MYSTERIES.
WHO KIDNAPPED JORDAN,
WHO'S EXPERIMENTING
WITH THE FREEZE FORMULA.
SAME ANSWER.
THE BLACK GLOVE SOCIETY.
THE BGS.
THE BEE GEES.
THEY RULE THE CITY
FROM THE SHADOWS.
THEY WANT TO LIVE FOREVER.
YOU KNOW.
USUAL BIG-MONEY
PERVERT STUFF.
SHE'S RIGHT.
JORDAN AND HER FRIENDS
WERE COLLECTING
INFORMATION ON
SOME BLACK
GLOVE SOCIETY.
SHE WAS GOING
TO USE HER SPEECH
FROM THE "30 UNDER 30"
TO UNMASK THE SOCIETY
AND SHUT IT DOWN.
NOW THAT IS
A GREAT WAY TO
MAKE YOURSELF
A TARGET OF GOTHAM'S
OLDEST SECRET SOCIETY OF
THE RICH AND POWERFUL.
I'LL SEND THIS
INFO TO LUKE
SO HE CAN CHECK
ON THE OTHERS
AND SEE IF
THEY'RE OK.
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
WHAT YOU WERE DOING?
YOU? SPECIAL AGENT PLAY-IT-SAFE?
SHE KNEW YOU'D TRY TO
TALK HER OUT OF IT.
UH, MARY?
I DON'T THINK HER
TEMPERATURE'S STABLE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THE FORMULA MUST BE
BREAKING DOWN
INSIDE OF HER BODY.
UGH. IF I COULD JUST
GET A SAMPLE OF THIS FORMULA,
I COULD FIGURE ALL OF THIS OUT.
IT'S TOO BAD
WE CAN'T JUST ASK HER
HOW TO FIND THE BEE GEES.
SHE WAS OBVIOUSLY
CLOSE ENOUGH TO SOMETHING
FOR THEM TO TURN HER
INTO A POPSICLE.
ALICE, YOU'RE
COMING WITH ME.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
I CAN'T JUST
WAIT FOR RYAN
TO SOLVE THIS FOR ME.
WE'RE GONNA SEARCH
JORDAN'S APARTMENT.
IF SHE'S GOT ANY OTHER
EVIDENCE ON BLACK GLOVE,
IT'LL BE HIDDEN THERE.
JUST GOT THE BLACK GLOVE
FILES FROM SOPHIE.
GIVE ME ONE SECOND TO SEE
WHAT JORDAN HAD ON HERE.
NOTHING THEY DO
IS DIGITAL.
MAYBE THAT'S HOW
THEY STAY OFF THE RADAR.
NO COMPUTERS.
NOTHING ON THE CLOUD.
NOTHING WE
CAN USE TO GET
A NAME OR A LOCATION?
WHAT ABOUT THE PEOPLE
JORDAN WAS TEXTING EARLIER?
M.I.A.
THEY ALL MET UP AT THE HOTEL
BUT THEN THEY ALL WENT DARK.
I BET THAT'S WHY
BLACK GLOVE DOES
THEIR FREEZE EXPERIMENTS
AT THE HOTEL.
ONE-STOP SHOPPING FOR EVERYONE
WHO HAS IT OUT FOR THEM.
OH, MY GOD.
THE CORONER IS TAKING
SOMEONE OUT OF
THE HOTEL IN PIECES.
PROBABLY ONE OF
JORDAN'S TEAM.
OK. I'M GOING UP
TO THE HOTEL.
WE GOTTA FIND
THE OTHER ONE.
DID YOU HAVE EYES ON MARQUIS
AROUND THE TIME THAT
JORDAN WENT MISSING?
- WHY?
- BGS IS BIG MONEY.
FLASHY GUYS DOING WHATEVER
IT TAKES TO STAY POWERFUL.
HE WOULD FIT PERFECTLY
INTO THAT CROWD.
FIND YOUR FRIEND'S SISTER?
YEAH. I DID. THANKS.
RIGHT WHERE YOU
SAID SHE'D BE.
GLAD I COULD
BE OF SERVICE.
I BET HE IS.
HOW'D HE KNOW
WHICH ROOM JORDAN WAS IN
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
HOW DID YOU KNOW
WHERE TO FIND HER?
I KNOW A GIRL WHO WORKS
AT THE FRONT DESK.
SHE ASKED AROUND FOR ME.
ONE OF THE HOUSEKEEPERS
SAID THAT SHE SAW
SOMEONE WHO LOOKED
LIKE JORDAN
BEING LED INTO
A BEDROOM
BY SOME OLDER GUY.
I'M NOT ACCUSING YOU. OK?
BUT LIKE I SAID,
I DON'T REALLY
KNOW YOU, MARQUIS.
I ACTUALLY
CAME TO APOLOGIZE.
FOR WHAT?
YOU THINK JADA'S
CRAZY, ANGRY,
CONTROL-FREAK THING
IS SOMETHING NEW?
THIS HAS BEEN
MY WHOLE LIFE.
ONLY CHILD. I WANTED
TO KNOW YOU SO BAD.
I THOUGHT,
FINALLY, MY SISTER.
WE GOT
EACH OTHER'S BACKS.
BUT I GUESS NOT.
WHAT THE HELL
WAS THAT ALL ABOUT?
I'LL FIGURE IT OUT
AFTER WE HELP JORDAN.
IS YOUR PHONE SERIOUSLY
NOT ON RIGHT NOW?
CHARLIE, SORRY.
SHE'S ON SILENT.
LOOK, I JUST
RAN INTO SOME
MOVERS AND SHAKERS
AT THE HOTEL,
SO, I GOTTA GET BACK
TO IT, OK?
LOOK.
RYAN, WHY IS HE SO PISSED?
BUILD YOU UP JUST SO
THEY CAN KNOCK YOU DOWN.
OK. BETTER GIVE ME
THE EXECUTIVE SUMMARY.
5 MINUTES AGO,
VESPER FAIRCHILD
BROKE THE SCOOP
THAT THE CEO
OF WAYNE ENTERPRISES
HAS BEEN DIVERTING
TENS OF MILLIONS
OF DOLLARS
INTO SECRET ACCOUNTS
FOR HER OWN USE.
JADA.
I JUST GOT OFF THE PHONE
WITH OUR CFO.
HE'S STARTED DOING
AN AUDIT OF OUR
ACCOUNTING SYSTEMS
AND HE AGREES
THAT THERE'S A PROBLEM.
WHAT? NO.
IT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
OK, LOOK.
I WILL TALK TO HIM
AND SORT THIS OUT,
BUT JUST NOT RIGHT NOW.
OH, DO YOU HAVE A MORE
DESPERATE CRISIS?
THEY SAY MULTITASKING IS
THE HARDEST PART
OF THE JOB.
NOT FOR MUCH LONGER.
OK. DON'T WORRY.
I WILL GET A BOX FOR
MY PERSONAL BELONGINGS.
GIRL, WHEN YOU CATCH
BERNIE MADOFF...
IN THIS CASE, YOU...
STEALING MONEY,
YOU DON'T FIRE HER.
YOU ARREST HER.
TELL ME SOMETHING
GOOD, LUKE.
MAYBE LIKE JADA JET
HACKED OUR SYSTEMS
AND FAKED ALL THAT
HIDDEN MONEY.
RYAN, SHE DIDN'T FAKE THIS.
WHY AM I THE LAST PERSON
TO KNOW THAT
I HAVE 8 FIGURES STASHED
UNDER A MATTRESS SOMEWHERE?
CAN YOU THINK OF
ANY OPERATIONS THAT
ARE EXTREMELY EXPENSIVE,
SECRETIVE,
AND CAN ONLY
BE AUTHORIZED BY
THE CEO OF
WAYNE ENTERPRISES?
BATMAN. AND NOW BATWOMAN.
THAT MONEY IS OUR
OPERATING BUDGET.
LOOK, I HAVE NO IDEA
HOW JADA GOT ACCESS
TO OUR ACCOUNTING SYSTEMS,
SO, THE ONLY GOOD NEWS IS
SHE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT
THE MONEY IS FOR,
JUST THAT SHE COULD
PIN IT ON YOU.
LUKE, I GIVE UP.
THERE'S NOTHING HERE.
THE COPS COULD
WALK IN ANY SECOND
AND I'M FREEZING
MY ASS OFF.
GCPD HAS THERMAL
IMAGING CAMERAS
ALL OVER THE CITY.
LET ME TAP IN, SEE IF
ANY OF THE OTHER ROOMS
HAVE ABNORMAL TEMPERATURES.
I'M NOT SEEING
ANY ICE BOXES.
LUKE? I'M SEEING A BUNCH
OF HEAT LAMPS HERE.
MAYBE THEY WERE GETTING READY
TO TRY THAWING HER.
IF THEY DID THAT
IN ANOTHER ROOM...
THEN ON THERMAL IMAGING
IT WOULD LOOK
MORE LIKE A SAUNA.
OK. BINGO.
GET READY TO SUIT UP.
OHH.
WHAT'S THE SITUATION?
DEAD BODY.
THEY TRIED TO UNFREEZE IT.
DIDN'T WORK.
POSITIVE I.D.
SHE'S THE OTHER ONE
IN JORDAN'S GROUP TEXT.
NO SIGN OF BLACK GLOVE.
I JUST RAN THE NAME OF THE
OTHER GUY IN THE GROUP TEXT.
ACCORDING TO THE GCPD,
HE WAS THE ONE
THEY JUST WHEELED
OUT OF THERE.
JORDAN'S THE ONLY
ONE LEFT.
HEY, NO SASS.
YOU LIVED IN A SEWER.
I'LL TAKE THE BEDROOM.
REMEMBER,
WE'RE LOOKING FOR
ANYTHING LOW-TECH.
ANYTHING CONNECTED
TO BLACK GLOVE.
IF JORDAN KNEW
IT WAS DANGEROUS,
IT WON'T BE
OUT IN THE OPEN.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE HERE.
HOW'S YOUR NECK?
THAT'S HURTFUL.
ARE YOU
TALKING TO SOMEONE?
OH, NO. HEH.
NO, I JUST LIKE TO
SAY THE DETAILS OUT LOUD.
PLEASE RESPECT
MY PROCESS AND
GO BACK TO
PICKING THROUGH
YOUR SISTER'S
UNDERWEAR DRAWER.
GO, GO.
YOU WANT MY TWO CENTS?
FIRST OF ALL,
THEY'RE MY TWO CENTS.
SECOND OF ALL, SHUT UP.
I'M WORKING.
YOU DIDN'T WANT TO READ
THOSE POSTCARDS.
YOU DON'T LIKE FEELING
THOSE LITTLE MACHINES
SWIM AROUND IN YOU
LIKE GUPPIES.
YOU BROKE MY DAMN NECK.
I'M SORRY.
DO I SEEM
A TEENSY BIT ON EDGE?
IT'S ONLY BECAUSE
THE FABRIC OF MY REALITY
IS COLLAPSING AROUND ME!
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE
KEEPING IT TOGETHER IN THERE?
OH, YEAH.
YOU KNOW,
JUST OVERCOMING
THE MOLD OF YOUR
SISTER'S DUSTY
MANIFESTOS.
MAYBE IF YOU KNEW
WHAT WAS REAL ABOUT
YOURSELF, BETH...
THE REST OF THE WORLD
WOULD FALL BACK INTO PLACE.
SHE UNMASKED THE BEE GEES.
OH, WOW.
THAT DOESN'T
BELONG TO YOU.
THANKS FOR THE WARNING.
JUST TAKING A SHOT HERE.
ARE YOU MAKE-BELIEVE?
I'M HERE FOR
EVERYTHING THAT WAS
SCANNED INTO
THE GIRL'S PHONE.
PRO TIP...
BUY A DOCUMENT SHREDDER.
AAH!
WHAT'S UP, LUKE?
YOU DIDN'T GIVE US
AN UPDATE
ON YOUR PROGRESS
WITH JORDAN.
I'M TRYING TO
KEEP HER STABLE
UNTIL SOMEONE
COMES THROUGH WITH
A SAMPLE OF
THE FORMULA.
YOU'VE HAD HER
LONG ENOUGH TO ANALYZE
EVERY ANGLE,
RUN EVERY TEST,
AND YOU'VE STILL
GOT NOTHING?
WOW. NO PRESSURE, HUH?
IF YOU GET TO JUDGE ME FOR HOW
I'M PERFORMING IN THE CLUTCH,
WHY CAN'T I DO
THE SAME FOR YOU?
I WAS TRYING TO HELP YOU,
NOT SCORE POINTS IN SOME
"WHO'S THE BEST HERO"
COMPETITION.
LOOK, I'M NOT
DUNKING ON YOU.
I'M JUST REMINDING YOU
THAT YOU
DECLARED YOURSELF
TEAM DOCTOR.
YEAH. I'M TRYING.
BUT I CAN BARELY
SEE STRAIGHT
BECAUSE I SPENT
THE NIGHT IN THE PARK,
WHICH NOBODY KNOWS ABOUT
BECAUSE NOBODY ACTUALLY CARES.
WHAT IS IT?
I CAN HEAR IT.
YOU JUST GOT AN IDEA, RIGHT?
ANIMALS NEVER EVOLVED
TO WITHSTAND FREEZING,
BUT PLANTS HAVE
ORGANIC MATERIAL
THAT'S PERFECTLY ADAPTED
TO FREEZING AND THAWING.
AND THEY SURVIVE WINTER
BY SYNTHESIZING
A TYPE OF ANTIFREEZE
INSIDE THEIR
VASCULAR TISSUE.
THE KEY IS TO THAW
FROM THE INSIDE,
NOT THE OUTSIDE.
AND YOU THINK THIS
COULD BE A WAY TO
SAFELY UNFREEZE JORDAN?
NO. I JUST THOUGHT IT WAS
A FUN FACT ABOUT PLANTS.
WHAT'S THAT SMELL?
GASOLINE.
ALICE. ALICE!
THAT'S A LITTLE
ON THE NOSE, BUT
THE BOOKS ARE
A NICE TOUCH.
HEY, WHERE'S YOUR KNIFE?
THE BEE GEES TOOK IT,
ALONG WITH ALL
THE EVIDENCE I FOUND
IN JORDAN'S HIDEY HOLE.
STOP TRYING TO MAKE
"BEE GEES" HAPPEN!
JEEZ. MISDIRECTED
ANGER, MUCH?
MISDIRECTED?
THIS IS COMPLETELY
YOUR FAULT.
- WHAT?
- YOU'RE ALICE,
A LEGIT SUPER VILLAIN.
THE ONLY REASON
THESE GUYS JUMPED YOU
IS BECAUSE YOU THOUGHT
YOU WERE TALKING TO
SOME GUY WHO
WASN'T EVEN THERE.
YEAH, I NOTICED.
SOMETIMES, I...
I'M NOT SURE WHAT'S
REAL AND WHAT'S NOT,
AND IT USED TO ONLY
HAPPEN AT ARKHAM,
BUT IT'S GETTING WORSE
AND I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
AND I DON'T KNOW ANYONE
WHO WANTS TO HELP ME.
OH, THAT'S ONE WAY
TO SOLVE MY PROBLEM.
SORRY, JORDAN.
HEY. HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
I WISH YOU HAD
TOLD ME.
I COULD'VE HELPED.
I WILL ALWAYS
SUPPORT YOU, JORDAN.
ALWAYS.
SHE'LL NEED
SOME MORE TIME
BEFORE SHE CAN TALK AGAIN.
HER ENTIRE BODY IS RESETTING.
AND I'M NOT GONNA LIE,
SHE MIGHT SMELL LIKE
CILANTRO FOR THE NEXT
COUPLE OF DAYS,
BUT SHE'S GONNA MAKE
A FULL RECOVERY.
OH, THANK GOODNESS.
CAN WE EAT NOW?
I AM SO SORRY, SOPH.
I SAID I'D HANDLE THIS.
AND WE STILL DON'T KNOW
WHO THESE PEOPLE ARE
OR WHAT THEY'RE DOING
WITH THE FREEZE SERUM.
JORDAN'S OK.
THAT'S ALL THAT MATTERS.
SO, HOW DID YOU KNOW
TO COME TO THE APARTMENT?
LUKE FIGURED OUT
THEY WERE AFTER
THE ORIGINAL DOCUMENTS
JORDAN HAD ON HER PHONE.
I'M NOT GOING TO LET
BLACK GLOVE
GET ANOTHER SHOT
AT HER.
YEAH, WELL, THEY ALMOST
BURNED ME AT THE STAKE,
SO, YOU'RE GETTING
MY HELP ON THIS.
AND ALICE'S, TOO,
WHETHER WE WANT IT
OR NOT.
MARY.
SO, ALICE TOLD ME
HER PSYCHOSIS
IS GETTING WORSE
AND SHE SUSPECTS
THE DOCTORS DON'T CARE.
HONESTLY?
IT'S ARKHAM.
WHATEVER MEDS
THEY'RE GIVING HER IN THERE
COULD BE CAUSING
A PSYCHOTIC BREAK
INSTEAD OF CURING IT.
IT'S GOING TO BE
EVERYONE'S PROBLEM
IF ALICE FULLY
LOSES HER MIND
BEFORE WE FINISH
THE JOB FOR MONTOYA.
BUT
HYPOTHETICALLY,
I COULD GET A SUPERVISED
WORK RELEASE FROM ARKHAM
AND SWEET MARY COULD MAKE SURE
I WAS TAKING MY PROPER MEDS.
I'M SURE THAT RY-RY
COULD CONVINCE RENEE-NAY
IT WAS FOR THE BEST.
YOU KNOW, ALL FOR THE
SAKE OF FIGHTING CRIME.
RIGHT. AND WHO'S
GONNA PUT UP WITH
THAT BABY-SITTING JOB?
SOMEONE WHO SLEEPS WITH
A GUN UNDER HER PILLOW.
WHAT DO YOU
SAY? ROOMIES!
HOW'S THE
OTHER CRISIS?
RESOLVED.
SO, YOU'LL BE
ONE-FOR-TWO TODAY.
YOU MIGHT THINK
YOU'RE HERE TO GIVE ME
BEST PRACTICES
FOR A PERP WALK,
BUT I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
I DID NOTHING WRONG.
OH, I BELIEVE YOU.
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN ON
THE JOB LONG ENOUGH
TO EMBEZZLE
A STAPLER,
LET ALONE
$30 MILLION.
I THINK YOU MADE THE
WRONG PERSON YOUR ENEMY
AND NOW YOU ARE
THE FALL GAL
FOR BRUCE WAYNE'S
MISDEEDS.
YOU THINK BRUCE WAYNE
STOLE FROM
HIS OWN COMPANY?
MR. WAYNE'S LEGACY
HAS BEEN
COMPLICATED SINCE
HE TOOK OVER
THE COMPANY.
WITH HIS ADDICTIONS,
MISBEHAVIORS,
AND DISAPPEARANCES,
LET'S JUST SAY
I'M USED TO
THE CHALLENGE OF
PUTTING LIPSTICK
ON A PIG.
WHAT'S THIS?
PRESS RELEASE
THAT WILL GO OUT
IN THE MORNING.
AFTER A THOROUGH REVIEW,
IT WAS DETERMINED
THAT THE MISSING MONEY
WAS PART OF A TOP-SECRET
DEFENSE CONTRACT
THAT YOU NEGOTIATED
WITH ARGUS.
CEO WILDER THOUGHT NO ONE
COULD KNOW ABOUT THIS
FOR NATIONAL
SECURITY REASONS,
AND DEEPLY REGRETS
NOT ALERTING
THE BOARD OF DIRECTORS.
ARGUS IS GONNA
GO ALONG WITH THIS STORY?
I HAVE
AN OLD FRIEND THERE.
HE'S DOING ME A FAVOR.
OK. THAT'S IT?
CRISIS AVERTED?
UNFORTUNATELY, NO.
THE STOCK PRICE
IS STILL CRATERING
BECAUSE SOMEONE
IS COORDINATING A CAMPAIGN
TO UNDERMINE
SHAREHOLDER CONFIDENCE.
IF WE DON'T
DO SOMETHING
TO RESTORE CONFIDENCE,
WE ARE AT RISK
OF A HOSTILE TAKEOVER.
THE BOARD OF
DIRECTORS IS
DEMANDING YOUR RESIGNATION.
IT IS THE BEST SHOT
WE HAVE
AT CONTAINING THE CRISIS.
OK, CHARLIE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
I SHOULD DO?
THAT'S UP TO YOU,
MS. WILDER.
BUT IN MY OPINION,
IF YOU REMAIN AS CEO,
WE WILL LOSE
THE COMPANY.
WELL, WE KNEW SHE WAS
CAPABLE OF THIS.
DID WE? BECAUSE
I'M NOT EVEN CLEAR
WHY THE WOMAN HATES ME SO DAMN MUCH.
I'M HER DAUGHTER!
AND I TOLD YOU THAT
DOES NOT MATTER TO HER.
OK, LOOK.
BRUCE WAS THE FACE
OF WAYNE ENTERPRISES.
BUT MY DAD
WAS HIS PARTNER.
AND BRUCE WOULD
ALWAYS SAY THAT
THE COMPANY
BELONGED TO LUCIUS
AS MUCH AS IT DID HIM.
RYAN, I CANNOT
LOSE THIS PLACE.
YOU THINK I CAN?
WHAT HAPPENS TO BATWOMAN
IF THERE'S NO CASH
TO PUT GAS
IN THE BATMOBILE?
I AM NOT LETTING
JADA TAKE MY CALLING.
SO, WHAT?
SO, EVEN THOUGH
NOBODY THINKS THAT
YOU'LL WIN,
YOU'RE JUST GONNA...
STAY AND FIGHT?
HAVE YOU MET ME?
OK.
FAILSAFE SUBROUTINE...
REACTIVATED.
NOW LET'S POWER CYCLE
THE BOOT LOADER.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU
AGAIN, SON.
DAD?
OH, MY GOD. UM...
I REALLY NEEDED
TO HEAR YOUR VOICE.
SO, THE COMPANY'S
UNDER ATTACK
AND I FEEL LIKE IF
WE LOSE WAYNE ENTERPRISES,
THAT'S JUST ANOTHER
PIECE OF YOU THAT'S
GONE FROM MY LIFE.
HELPING WAYNE ENTERPRISES
IS BEYOND THE SCOPE
OF WHAT I CAN HELP WITH.
YEAH. I KNOW.
WE'RE ALREADY
MAKING A PLAN.
I JUST... I NEEDED TO KNOW
WHY YOU STOPPED
TALKING TO ME.
YOU REPAIRED THE SYSTEM
FAULT IN THE O.S.
THAT HAD BEEN
BLOCKING THIS A.I.
FROM NORMAL OPERATION.
I DIDN'T REPAIR ANYTHING.
I JUST
TURNED THE FAILSAFE
BACK ON.
LUCAS, THIS A.I.
IS NOT DESIGNED TO RUN
INDEPENDENT OF
THE FAILSAFE.
IT HAS NO PURPOSE
IF IT'S NOT
EMPOWERED TO ACT
IN YOUR BEST INTEREST.
RIGHT. OK, SO,
ONCE A DAD, ALWAYS A DAD.
WHAT DID YOU WANT
TO ASK ME?
WELL, A FRIEND OF MINE
KIND OF ALREADY
GAVE ME THE ANSWER, BUT...
I NEED TO HEAR IT
FROM THE MAN HIMSELF.
UM...
I'M NOT READY TO WEAR
THE SUIT, AM I?
NO, SON.
YOU'RE NOT.
SO, WHY'D YOU HAVE ME
MEET YOU HERE?
NOTHING LEFT TO LOSE?
JADA WANTS WAYNE
ENTERPRISES, DOESN'T SHE?
LOOK... I'M SORRY
YOU HAD TO FACE
JADA'S WRATH,
AND THAT I HAD SOMETHING
TO DO WITH THAT,
BUT SHE'S HAD ME SIGN
A THOUSAND NDAs OVER THE YEARS,
SO, CAN'T REALLY
TALK ABOUT
COMPANY BUSINESS.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO SIBLINGS
HAVING EACH
OTHER'S BACKS?
WHAT HAPPENED WAS YOU
WEREN'T INTERESTED.
I AM NOT LETTING OUR MOM
TAKE OVER
WAYNE ENTERPRISES.
DO YOU THINK
THE TWO OF US
COULD STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST JADA?
IF WE PLEDGED
TO WORK TOGETHER.
IT'S DEADLINE DAY,
MY FRIEND.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE FOR ME?
I HAVE THE ANSWER
YOU'VE BEEN SEARCHING FOR.
AND IT WORKS
THE WAY I ASKED?
IT WASN'T AN EASY PROCESS,
BUT YES.
WE WERE ABLE TO ADAPT
VICTOR FRIES' RESEARCH
INTO A NEW FORMULA
THAT CAN SAFELY
FREEZE AND UNFREEZE
ORGANIC MATERIAL.
WHAT MADE THE PROCESS
SO DIFFICULT?
OUR ARRANGEMENT IS
THE BLACK GLOVE SOCIETY
COMMISSIONS US TO
ACHIEVE THE IMPOSSIBLE.
BUT OUR TERMS
WERE NON-NEGOTIABLE.
YOU DO NOT INQUIRE
ABOUT OUR METHODS,
NOR OUR IDENTITIES.
YOU DON'T WANT TO TELL ME
WHAT LINES YOU CROSS
TO "ACHIEVE
THE IMPOSSIBLE."
YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHAT LINE I CROSSED?
THE FINAL BREAKTHROUGH
CAME FROM
A RIVAL RESEARCH TEAM.
I STOLE THEIR IDEA.
AS LONG AS THAT'S
THE EXTENT OF IT,
I'M A VERY
HAPPY CUSTOMER.
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH A LITTLE
CORPORATE ESPIONAGE.
SO. NOW THAT YOU
HAVE THE ABILITY
TO PUT ANYONE'S LIFE
ON PAUSE INDEFINITELY,
YOU JUST GIVE ME
THE WORD
AND I'LL MAKE IT HAPPEN.
OH, I WILL.
AND IT WON'T BE
A LONG WAIT.
THE TIME HAS COME
FOR MY SON MARQUIS
TO TAKE HIS
LEAVE OF ABSENCE.
GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD.