Okay. Get on her, get on her!
Go!
Okay...
Shakes her defender
pulls up from way downtown,
fires, and...
misses, oh.
- Brick City, baby.
- Shut up.
Yo, come on, let's go.
Hang on a second.
What the...
Oh, hell, no!
Help. Help me.
Oh, my God.
You're standing
on the freaking evidence.
Ma'am, this area is off-limits.
I'm gonna pretend
you didn't just call me "ma'am"
and instead ask you to leave.
This case belongs to City Hall now.
Pack it up, boys.
Freak Patrol's on the scene.
Her ambiguous yet far-reaching power
supersedes ours.
Miss you too, detective.
- All right, let's go.
- Take him to the clinic on Bennett.
Ask for Mary Hamilton.
Who is it now, Montoya?
Pollen Boy? Candyman?
Tell the commissioner to prep
for all hands on deck.
Things are about to get ugly
around here.
Victim is Chris Hayner.
Tricorner resident found encased
in a beehive in Robinson Park.
You think someone
went through the trouble
of filling a shed with flowers
to draw in bees
to, what, sting this guy to death?
I think the perp literally bloomed
the flowers themselves
weaponizing the natural world
around them.
What am I missing?
Poison Ivy.
More specifically, her new host.
Alice turned over Ivy's vine
to me yesterday.
It was dead, meaning
it had already infected someone.
I think whoever did this
is that someone.
How did you get Poison Ivy's vine?
While you were slurping caviar
off of Mommy's fine china
some of us were in the field,
protecting this city.
And you just so happen
to stumble across a Batman trophy
while you were taking a stroll
through the park.
The cherry blossoms are so gorgeous
this time of year.
Trust me, I already tried
to get it out of her.
Why aren't you telling me
what you're not telling me?
You lost me on the double negative.
Guys, we don't have time for this.
Trust me, I tried.
Found the vic's phone at the scene.
It's passcode-protected.
But I think there's a good chance
he had contact
with whoever did this to him.
My computer can crack his passcode.
Good. I told Mary Hamilton to give me
a call as soon as our vic wakes up.
You sent him to Mary Hamilton?
She's been overseeing
all the River Rogue cases.
Is there a problem?
No. No problem at all.
In fact, Mary Hamilton
is the perfect person
to help us with this case.
I'm gonna go check
on the vic's progress.
Because you care about
a stranger's life all of a sudden?
You're right. I don't.
Let's you and I go sit
in the Batcave together
and watch the computer
tediously cycle
through all
the anti-encryption ciphers.
Have fun with Mary.
Will do.
Sophie, make yourself at home.
Sorry. Hope you don't mind.
Alice spilled cherry soda
all over my laptop.
Besides, you have more eyes
in this city than I do.
Black Glove's mercenaries
stay invisible
by doing things
the old-fashioned way.
They're off the grid,
they're off the cloud.
Surprised
they used electricity at all.
Found this surveillance
of Jordan's attacker
leaving her apartment,
but I lost him a block later.
So you're waiting for him
to show up on cameras again?
Unless your mom
miraculously came clean
and offered up her Rolodex?
I figured when you didn't call
last night
confronting her
about what these guys
did to my sister was a dead end.
So it's just you and me
and Crispy Joe's wontons.
My mom wasn't responsible
for what happened to Jordan.
And you believe her?
You believe her.
And now, I need you to believe me.
My mom isn't the monster
you think she is.
I think you should drop it.
Ryan, my sister had evidence.
I mean, a drawing
of Victor Fries' cryochamber
was faxed
directly to your mom's office.
I am not saying
she didn't initiate the project.
So you're saying she is involved.
I am saying that Jada promised me
she had no idea
people were going to get hurt.
And that's good enough?
Three of Jordan's friends died
because of your mom's involvement
with the freeze serum.
Jordan is still in recovery.
What happened was horrible.
I am not saying it's okay.
Then, why aren't you wondering why?
And why does she want it?
And why aren't you stopping her?
Because it's complicated.
I promise you, I will tell you
everything when I can.
When you can?
Ryan, it's me.
What does she have over you?
Let me help. I can get you out of it.
She doesn't have anything over me.
Then, why are you protecting her?
Sophie.
I just need you to trust me on this.
- Because she's your mom.
- It's not that simple.
Oh, really?
Because you're making it sound
pretty freaking simple.
Tell me there's a jar of this
somewhere.
Why did Batwoman send you here
to torture me?
Oh, she didn't. I volunteered.
Of course, you did.
Apparently, this is the work
of a Poison Ivy wannabe.
The question is, what kind of monster
would entomb a man
in a swarm of ravenous bees?
You know it's bad
if it makes me cringe.
Oh, I have an idea.
Why don't you leave and go find out?
That's the thing, steppy.
I think I already know
who this disturbed creature is.
You.
I see.
You're having delusions again.
And instead of admitting it
like a normal person
you're gaslighting me
to avoid being vulnerable
when I tell you I stopped caring.
Oh, sweet, naive Mary.
Look around.
You've turned your clinic
into Jumanji.
You're downing water
like you just ran
the Gotham City Marathon.
And if you think that
that is anything
other than a Poison Ivy rash
you should give back
that shiny medical degree.
Seriously? Look at me.
I'm Dr. Mary Hamilton.
You actually think
I'm capable of hurting anyone?
Much less doing this?
Chris?
Chris? It's okay. You're safe now.
- Help me!
- Hey, relax.
Please... get away from me.
Chris, I'm your doctor.
You're safe now.
I'm taking care of you.
Taking care of me?
You did this to me.
As I was saying?
Okay, team meeting
in the literal dead of the night.
So why are we here?
So you know how we have
the Bat Team rules
and the first rule is holding
each other accountable.
Yeah.
So...
I'm...
You're...
Oh, wow, I thought watching Kate
come out was torture.
Wait, you're coming out?
What? No.
Oh, in a way.
I'm not coming out
because I'm not gay.
But that's beside the point.
Mary, my God.
I'm Poison Ivy.
And I know
what you all must be thinking.
"Mary, that's impossible
because you're so normal
and compassionate.
So how could you become
some plant-whispering
attempted murderer?"
Then I realized I can't even remember
where I was earlier today.
It's because I was
in some fugue state
torturing Chris Hayner,
who I don't even know.
I'm sorry. What?
See, that little worker bee
in the hive
when he cracked his eyes open
he blamed Queen Mary
for turning him into an EpiPen ad.
Then he's seeing things.
I mean, his eyes
were practically swollen shut.
And he'd just experienced
a major trauma.
Okay, then explain
my sudden obsession with plants.
You're a doctor. You care for things.
Or my sudden, constant,
unquenchable thirst.
You're dehydrated.
Mary, you work in the clinic
all day and night
you don't eat or sleep
and you're always putting
everyone's needs before your own...
Guys?
Why were Chris Hayner's
last three texts
to Mary this morning?
And we're all on the same page.
Well, that wasn't
an excruciating process.
You knew Mary was infected
by the vine.
That's why you're being so coy
in Montoya's office.
I just figured
the last thing anyone needed
was for Mary to end up
on Renee's wall of weird.
Oh, muting the boss.
I'm sure that's gonna end
really well.
Montoya doesn't need to know
anything about this.
Okay. I see.
It's fine when we throw Alice
in Arkham
but, oh, poor, sweet, innocent Mary.
Yeah, we should protect her
at all costs.
What are you doing?
What one does when they realize
they can control
Mother-freaking-Earth.
I nearly killed someone
and I don't know why
or when this infection
is gonna make me transform again.
And until we figure it out,
I am a threat to everyone.
- So I'm staying right here.
- (Not me.)
Well, you can take the girl
out of the GCPD.
Looks like you got the same partner.
Sophie Moore.
Only a fellow workaholic would assume
I'd be at the office at 2.00am.
This is an office?
Wouldn't have guessed.
I mean, I thought Detective Montoya
was on track
to be the next commissioner.
Now, you're sharing a basement
with a leaky pipe? Ouch.
At least I have a job.
I quit The Crows by choice.
Right before Kane's own agents
tried to kill him?
Oh, real profile in courage.
I'm here to let you return a favor.
Oh, excuse me. Then, please, go on.
I'd love to hear
what you've done for me
other than flash your Crows badge
to steal my best cases.
If I weren't willing to babysit Alice
you'd never be able to prove
to the mayor
that you're capable of collecting
all these Batman weapons.
And we both know, without Alice
none of these cases
are getting solved.
Fine. I'll bite. What?
Someone experimented on my sister
with a variant of Victor Fries's
freeze serum.
I need all the data
your Task Force collected
on Fries and that serum.
We don't have half
of what Batwoman does.
Aren't you pals?
Go shine a flashlight in the air.
I would. Except we're not
seeing eye to eye on this.
Drama.
You want me to get two straws?
What do you know about
the Black Glove society?
Specifically him.
This guy led the experiments.
Is your sister okay?
Do you actually care?
If your sister survived
what they did to her
then I'd count my lucky stars.
And then I'd forget
I ever heard of Black Glove.
Well, what do you know?
Absolutely nothing.
Except that everyone who knows
anything about Black Glove
usually ends up dead.
Be careful, Moore.
There are worse things
than ending up like me.
Do you remember meeting him
on Twinge?
I didn't even know I was on Twinge.
I've never seen this guy before
in my life.
Are your eyes green
in your profile picture?
No. I think it's just bad lighting.
Maybe he was stalking me
or maybe he was some date rape guy
and I found out about it.
It seems like
he just wasn't that into you.
Yeah, according to your DMs,
which I merely skimmed for keywords
he said you seemed...
sweet.
So you suffocated him in honey.
Clever girl.
I think I wanna date Poison Ivy Mary.
Hold on.
Rejection?
I almost took an innocent man's life.
Okay, Mary's right.
That's a pretty screwed-up reason
to nearly drown a guy.
I don't know.
Is it though?
I mean, I've never been accused
of being sweet
but it's basically like saying,
you know
"You're pleasant
but instantly forgettable."
It's like the "beige" of compliments.
- The "swipe left" of niceties...
- We get it.
You don't really think
that's how people see you, right?
Hey, do you remember going
to a hardware store this morning?
Should I?
Well, you bought a flowering pot,
fertilizer, and a watering can.
And according to your phone's
geo data
once you left the store,
you went to a vacant lot in Burnside.
Please don't tell me
I hurt anyone else.
Why didn't you say anything
about Mary?
I was wondering
how this would end up my fault.
Obviously, you knew something was up.
How did you figure it out?
The question isn't
how I figured it out.
It's how the hell you didn't.
You're her roommate.
You have a billion dollars
of Bat Tech at your disposal.
And your number two
is a certifiable genius.
One of you should have noticed.
Fertilizer bag is empty
but the ground's not disturbed.
Nothing was planted.
Why was Mary here?
Mary Hamilton, you dirty girl.
He's still alive.
Oh, well, it's only her first day.
- Wonder what this guy did to Mary.
- I don't know
but he tried to kill Sophie and me
and freeze Sophie's sister.
Somehow Mary managed to turn
one of Black Glove's
most dangerous operatives
into a garden turnip.
I'm not sure if that's impressive
or just really, really bad.
I don't suppose you have a Bat-shovel
on that belt.
Sorry, how did I track down
an elusive black-ops organization?
You tracked the PO box
Virgil Getty was using
through the company that sold him
the cryogenic medical supplies
that he used
on the freeze serum victims.
Sophie's been a bloodhound
with this guy.
I'm sure she tried that.
Yeah, well, Sophie doesn't have an MD
after her name.
Looks like
Dr. Hamilton used her title
to bypass privacy laws.
Violation of medical ethics?
Harley Quinn, here you come.
Perhaps someone should tell Sophie
that the guy
who tried to burn us alive
and freeze her sister to death
is hanging from a sewer pipe
under Wayne?
No, we have enough problems
without Sophie finding more.
Well, "Moore" is literally her name.
And as a victim of Sophie's backhand,
I'd say she can handle herself.
I said she stays out of it.
Okay.
Can we go back to me freaking out
over the fact that I'm turning
into an uber-villain against my will?
Why is this happening?
Poison Ivy is an eco-terrorist.
Neither of your victims
had any public record
of actively hurting the environment.
Yeah, but the Bat-villain weapons
don't necessarily mean the same MO.
Liam Crandle
didn't have the same agenda
as the OG Mad Hatter.
That's a good point.
Chris called you sweet,
you dipped him in honey.
Virgil froze Jordan
so you used Mother Nature
to immobilize him.
So maybe the chemical pheromones
from the poison ivy
allow me to communicate with nature
while heightening the things
that I'm passionate about?
Like justice?
Well, seeing as the MO tracks
and I killed your mother
I'm really not looking forward
to being turned into a cabbage.
So we should find out exactly
what turns Dr. Jekyll
into
Mrs. Hide-My-Victims-Under-A-Pot.
Damn it.
What does she want?
You, my dear.
Dead or alive.
Making house calls now?
Why didn't you tell me
you found another Poison Ivy vic?
It's 5 in the morning.
I figured you were asleep.
I don't sleep, Ryan.
Especially when someone's out there
with Pam's abilities.
- Where's the vic?
- In my custody.
Yeah, well, I need to talk to him.
I need to know what he saw,
what he knows.
He's unconscious at the moment.
When he's talking, I will call you.
Oh, just like Chris Hayner?
Is that a coincidence
or a convenience?
You wanted to partner
with Batwoman, right?
Then you need to trust my process.
Ryan is flail-ling.
What did you mean
Renee wanted me dead or alive?
Renee and Poison Pam
have a backstory.
What kind of backstory?
I don't wanna be a gossip.
- Spill.
If you insist.
So...
They met, fell madly in love.
Kissy...
Then Pam fell victim
to some evil scientist's experiment.
Obviously, Pam's metamorphosis
into Little Shop of Horrors
got in the way of sexy time
which was big problem for Renee
as she was a GCPD detective.
Crisis of the heart. Boring...
Ultimately, Renee called Batman
who convinced her to lure
the love of her life into his trap.
Why would someone
infected with poison ivy
target a Black Glove operative?
It doesn't makes sense
unless he had a personal connection
to him.
If I knew, I would tell you.
Would you?
Because I'm beginning to feel like
you're hiding things from me, Ryan.
Where's the vic?
That's really intense.
So Renee sold out
the love of her life to Batman?
And he buried her deep underground
away from water and sunlight
to shrivel up and not die.
Can you imagine going without
that skin cream for all those years?
Imagine what she'd do
to someone she barely even knows.
Okay. I think Mary's heard enough.
What? I'm not trying to scare her.
It's just Liam ended up in Arkham.
Killer Croc in a cage
and Nora Fries
would rather face death
over being held captive again.
I just think
we are doing ourselves a disservice
to deny the predictable outcome
of anyone who comes in contact
with Batman's trophies.
As a girl who spent
over a decade of her life
locked in a small room
I just want you to avoid
ending up the way they did.
Watching the woman I love
go from this compassionate,
selfless person
into this thing that could justify
killing dozens of people
it broke me, Ryan.
And now she's infected someone else.
To... To pretend like
I don't know how this ends
to not do everything in my power
to stop it.
It wouldn't be fair to me,
to this city
or to the Pam I used to know.
Just call me when your guy wakes up.
We need to figure out
what my trigger is.
Maybe it's a word
or a series of words.
Actually,
I'm starting to feel a little funny.
Okay. Funny how?
My vision's a little blurry.
Okay. Maybe you're dehydrated.
Renee's on my ass.
We don't have a lot of time
to figure this out.
We could ask Sophie to ask Virgil
if he said or did anything
that triggered Mary.
Sophie's not with Virgil.
What did you do?
So...
Sophie has been a great roommate.
You know, she puts my dishes away.
She cleans my clothes
with that fabric softener
that doesn't irritate
my sensitive skin.
Alice, what did you do?
Sophie really wanted
to interrogate Virgil
and I didn't want to keep secrets
from my roomie.
You're an idiot.
You have no idea
what you've just done.
So sue me for having guilt
for once in my life.
Seriously, just stop talking.
I don't get it.
Why can't Sophie know
where Virgil is?
I'll be back.
Call me if anything changes here.
Where are you going?
To stop Sophie
from making a huge mistake.
Hello again.
I know.
You thought you burned me alive.
But nope, I lived.
To do the same to you.
I've got some questions
about your employer.
Who hired you to take my sister?
Let me rephrase that.
Was it Jada Jet?
Technically, I was hired
by Marla Elliot decades ago.
Elliot. As in Tommy Elliot?
His mother.
Thought Tommy had
behavioral problems.
Well, she got that right
since he turned
into that psycho, Hush.
Before that, she formed a group
of other parents with bad seed kids.
Swapped horror stories,
discussed treatments, meds, whatever.
Like secret group therapy
for rich people
to talk about their screwed-up kids.
I don't know of any self-help groups
that employ a militia.
They're called Black Glove
because they don't leave a trace.
Titans of industry
spending millions on R&D
to fix their kids' brains?
Not great for public image.
Yeah, and neither
is injecting twenty-somethings
with fatal freeze serum.
My clients would agree with you.
Which is exactly why we clean up
after ourselves.
My sister nearly died!
Three of her friends did!
Why? What does Jada want?
Enough!
Seriously?
I have to find out from Alice
that you found this guy?
I said I would tell you everything.
When?
When it's safe.
Safe from what?
Safe from what, Ryan?
From her? From Jada? Who?
Sorry.
You want my trust?
You're gonna have to earn it.
Because right now, it looks like
you're taking the side of a woman
who sanctioned murder over me,
your actual friend.
No, no, no!
He's dead.
Guess you get to keep
mommy's secret a little longer.
When Bruce met Pam Isley,
she was Poison Ivy 24/7.
Well, wherever he put her
obviously contained her, right?
Maybe the key is figuring out
how he did that.
This is before my time
but from what he told the press
they put her in a place
no one would ever find her.
It doesn't even affect you
anymore, does it?
What doesn't affect me?
Oh, being second fiddle
to whatever other dramas
going on in Ryan's life.
Wow, you know what, it's funny.
I don't think we actually
need you here anymore.
Alice, so if you like
to go sniff your fluff and fold,
now would be a great time.
Are neither of you concerned?
That our leader, Batwoman,
left her bestie
infected, vulnerable, terrified
to go "help" a woman
who literally shares a bedroom wall
with a serial killer.
She knows what she's doing.
Oh, I know she knows
what she's doing.
But do you know what she's doing?
See, Ryan doesn't care about
protecting Sophie from Virgil, no.
She cares about protecting
Virgil from Sophie.
Specifically, his secrets.
Presumably, because
they're about her mother.
A woman whose needs she,
once again, prioritizes
- over the Bat Team.
- Ryan, wouldn't do that.
She already did, Luke.
Which has me wondering
if it's only a matter of time
before Ryan waltzes
into Renee's office
with Mary in bat cuffs.
Are you joking?
Ryan wouldn't arrest her best friend.
She's gonna find a way to fix this.
Good morning, sunshine.
I was wondering
when you'd come out to play.
You figured out
sunlight was my trigger.
Well, they don't call me
a supervillain for nothing.
But Batty will be home soon
so I hope you know what you're doing.
Why are you helping me?
Well, why does anyone help anyone?
To accrue favors owed.
But until I redeem this one,
I need you to be careful.
Once you slither out
of this Batcave...
Renee Montoya's gonna
be hunting you down
like a gardener with a weed whacker.
- Montoya.
- Oh, hi.
Someone told me to call this number
with a possible tip
about Poison Ivy's sighting.
Where are you? I'll be right there.
Gotham City Botanical Gardens.
Renee Montoya.
Mary?
You need to get out of here,
it's not safe.
Trust me, I'm well aware.
Nowhere around you is safe, Renee.
Who are you?
I'm the one who called in the tip.
Virgil's dead, Alice.
I hope you're happy.
- Luke? Luke.
- Yeah, I'm okay.
What happened?
Did Alice do something with Mary?
- The sunlight.
- What?
Sunlight is her trigger.
She's not Mary anymore.
Where did you get infected?
At the park? The river?
Where was the vine, Mary?
It's not a homing pigeon
for the brokenhearted, Ray-Ray.
You don't whisper "Pamela Isley"
into the leaves
and follow as it slithers its way
to her secret burial site.
And you know about Pam?
Enough to know that
she doesn't want you to find her.
Look, you need to come with me
so I can get you help.
Is that what I need?
Did you use that soft, gentle tone
to lure Poison Pam into captivity?
No.
She was out of control.
And you're not there yet,
let's keep it that way.
What do you think she thinks about
down there.
I mean, besides freedom and water
and how her veins scrape together
like sandpaper.
Easy.
Let's not make this ugly.
She thinks about how much
she hates you, Renee.
Mary, come with me now
and no one will get hurt.
Or stay. And only you do.
Mary, please don't do this.
Mary's phone just pinged
at the old Gotham Botanical gardens.
- I need to get there.
- I'm coming with you.
I thought you said
you weren't ready to wear the suit.
Actually, my dad decided that.
I may not be ready to wear the suit,
but I'm not ready to lose Mary,
either.
My dad will understand.
If he doesn't, I'm sure
I'll hear about it on the way.
Let's get out of here.
I'm reading some sort of energy here.
Yeah, definitely picking up
one abnormally high thermo presence
in these trees.
You feel like you're being watched?
Tiny bit.
Yellow roses.
Yellow roses symbolize friendship.
Mary knows us better than anyone.
She knew we'd track her phone.
Do you think
she wants us to find her?
I think she want to draw us out.
Batwoman to Batwing.
Batwing. Where are you?
You good?
Across the dome.
My shoulder's jacked.
She can't be far. Stay alert.
Okay. What's up, Dad?
No comment from the peanut gallery?
I got my ass blown off from my feet,
and you got nothing to say, huh?
Dad? Dad, you there?
What kind of hero
still needs his daddy?
East garden. I found Mary.
- I think.
- Please, you didn't find me.
I found myself, and here I am.
Look, we're gonna find a way
to fix this, Mary.
We're gonna help you.
Everyone keeps saying that.
They're gonna help me.
Help me, what? Be less happy?
Less myself? Less alive?
This isn't you and you know it.
You're not hearing me, Luke.
This is exactly me.
Just without the part
that does everything you want.
Dad? Dad! Help! Help me!
You dad's gone, Luke.
I took out your failsafe
and the AI that came with it.
I figured Lucius Fox's brain
could really open up
some doors for me in the future.
That's my dad!
You don't need him.
You said it yourself,
you don't have PTSD.
You don't need a team doctor.
And you certainly
don't need your daddy
telling you what you can
and can't do.
Am I right?
Well, well, well.
Finally, I have your full attention.
I've been a crappy friend.
I'm sorry, Mary.
Friend?
You never asked me how I am.
You never give me any of your time.
You give more of yourself to a woman
who literally gave you away
and said she wanted nothing
to do with you
than you do your own teammate.
And that is not friendship.
Okay. Mary, we need to go now.
Look, these cops won't care
who you are
or what happened to you.
They will just lock
your ass up for good.
Mary, come with me.
I'm done with team spirit.
It's time
you heard my voice for once.
Loud and clear.
Mary!
You've been so wrapped up
in your own drama, Ryan.
Mary.
It's time you got wrapped up in mine
for once.
All right. Don't flinch.
Let me help.
You called the cops?
You knew who we're looking for
all along, didn't you?
Look, you don't understand.
Mary's our best friend.
No, you two don't understand.
Your best friend is currently
the most dangerous person in Gotham.
And you just set her lose
on the city.
You need a hand?
I need a Mary.
I thought...
I could reconnect with my family
and handle bat duties but...
I became oblivious
to what was going on with Mary.
I don't know what's worse,
that she felt that way
or that we didn't realize it.
She may be infected
with Poison Ivy...
but that anger was all her.
I don't think an apology
is gonna fix this.
Everything she said to me was true.
She tried to tell me
about the incident at the park.
And I was so distracted
with my family drama, I didn't
even give her the time of day.
This is my fault.
What's the damage?
Torn rotator cuff.
I deserve it.
I didn't take her warning
about the suit seriously.
Okay, well,
we're taking her seriously now.
- Any word from Alice?
- Not yet.
Yeah, I told Sophie to shoot me
a text when she gets home.
In the meantime,
have every Wayne satellite
scanning for her face 24/7
until we find her.
Okay, and then what?
It's an infection, right?
We make a cure.
How do you supposed we do that
without our team scientist?
I call in a favor.
Better make that two.
Bad day?
Not that I ever need a new excuse.
You?
Yup.
Oh, hope I'm not making it worse.
Believe it or not, Montoya...
there are other people I'd rather
not be drinking with right now.
Nicest thing anyone
said to me all day.
Jada? It's Ryan.
I need your help.
Mary, Mary, quite contrary.
How does your garden grow?
Quite well it seems
from all the sirens
I've been hearing around town.
It's fully electric, Steppy.
Was that supposed to impress me?
Yeah, considering
it was 10 times harder to hotwire.
So, you going to tell me what you did
to everyone's favorite cellar dweller
from the Mayor's office or what?
On the road.
There's that patented Dr. Hamilton
bedside manner, all warm and chatty.
Get in.