(theme music playing)
CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh! (screams)
(techno-pop music playing)
WOMAN: Welcome to another
episode of Padz...
where we go inside the mega-mansions
of today's hot, young celebrities.
This was today?
The girl was supposed to call.
Oh, let's get this over with.
Here's the recliner where
Don Adams and Shelley Winters...
made beautiful music together.
It should be in a museum,
but museums don't want it.
And here's my pool.
I don't swim, so that's where
I throw my shrimp shells.
Krustofski.
Why, look, it's my celebrity neighbor,
Elliott Gould.
Your monkey bit my kid again.
Well, if he would stop wearing
the banana suntan lotion...
-Say hello to Bob, and Carol.
-(groans)
-And Ted and Alice.
KRUSTY: Oh, that's it, Gould.
And you keep your lousy dog off my lawn.
GIRL (thinking): Dear diary...
(gasps)
"I have a crush on Kenny."
Ha! That's me.
You would like me, loser.
(laughing)
ANNOUNCER: Girls,
don't let this happen to you.
Get the Turbo Diary from Girltech.
No one can read your secrets except you.
(computerized voice) Unauthorized user.
Access denied.
(screams)
Turbo Diary, I love that I bought you.
ANNOUNCER: Get your
Turbo Diary from Girltech.
Girltech is a division of Boytech.
Hey, I could really use one of those.
No arguments here.
Man, I really come off
like a jerk in this thing.
(Marge humming)
Mom, Dad, my birthday's coming up
and Girltech Turbo Diaries
are in stores now.
Lisa, nobody likes a shill.
-Just buy me the frigging toy.
-(chuckles)
I love that little shill.
-Let's get her that diary.
-I agree.
A girl should have her own private diary.
I had to share mine with my uncle.
HOMER: Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
Dad, you can't eat all those free samples.
We've gotta get Lisa's present.
Watch and learn.
(growling and snorting)
More free samples.
Dad, you ate all the free samples.
Now you're eating men's slacks.
Eh, it's still better than Indian food.
Oh.
One Turbo Diary, please.
Trying to keep those
crushes secret, eh, Romeo?
It's not for me. I'm not a girl like you.
Well played. Oh.
I'm sorry, sir, but I just sold
the last Turbo Diary to that guy.
Finally, Smithers,
a device worthy of storing
my top-secret enemies list.
I'm ready, sir.
Number one, the Kingston Trio.
Ugh. Number two...
(computerized voice) Unauthorized user.
Access denied.
(Homer screams)
Oh. Now what am I gonna get Lisa?
Sir, I can offer you
this Tickle Me Krusty...
the most popular toy of 1999.
(squeaks)
DOLL: I'm anatomically correct.
Go ahead, take a peek.
(squeaks)
I wonder what mommy's
medicine tastes like.
Lisa's not gonna want that.
Oh, what can I get her?
Shop of the morning, Homer.
Just call me Mall Flanders.
(chuckles)
What are you buying? Jerk stuff?
Oh, you betcha.
This kiosk sells personalized movies.
I had one made starring little Rod.
NARRATOR: Kiosk Productions presents...
an outer space adventure starring you.
One day while flying your spaceship,
you saw a planet and decided to land.
(narrator's voice) Greetings.
I am Commander...
(Flander's voice) Rod.
Welcome, earthling.
What are your hobbies?
(narrator's voice) My hobbies include...
(Flander's voice) Being quiet during trips
clapping with songs, and diabetes.
Sounds like fun!
Let's party!
(lively, canned tune plays)
Hey, your kid is in the movie!
And the movie knows his name!
Maybe Lisa will like this
better than the diary.
Stupid Flanders, you're a genius.
A laser pointer.
Thanks, Bart.
It's really cool.
You can point a red dot
at people's crotches
from really far away.
Hmm.
There appears to be a red dot
on my trouser fronts.
I'd better lower them. (sighs)
The dot also appears
to be on my underpants.
Well, down they go.
(police siren)
Hey, buddy,
you better get that red dot checked out.
My uncle died of crotch dot.
OK, Lisa.
Now, open the present
from your father and me.
Hmm, hmm.
I wonder what this could be.
I think you'll be pleasantly surprised.
Could it be some kind of book?
Well, yes and no.
Mostly no.
What?
You were supposed
to get her that stupid diary!
But it's a personalized video
about my favorite little star--
Lisa Simpson.
Well, this could be fun.
Let's watch it.
(tinny music plays)
(female voice) Howdy, pardners.
My name is Sheriff...
(Homer's voice) Lisa Simpson.
I sure am hungry for my favorite food...
(Homer's voice) McNuggets.
I don't like McNuggets.
I'm a vegetarian!
Still?
Then you're not going to like
your other present.
(cowboy theme plays)
(female voice) Why, it's my best friend...
(Homer's voice) Maggie.
Huh?
Bad news, Sheriff...
(Homer's voice) Lisa Simpson.
Some Indians took all the...
(Homer's voice) McNuggets.
Mm, McNuggets.
(Homer groaning happily)
(female voice)
I'll get those no-good Indians.
Just as sure as my favorite book is...
(Homer's voice) Magazines!
(Homer snoring)
BART: Wake up, Dad.
(Homer's voice) Huh? What?
Dad! That information is all wrong!
Maggie's a baby, not my best friend.
(crying)
You don't know anything about me!
(sobbing)
-Wh...
-(door slamming)
Maggie, you're her best friend.
Go talk to her.
(thudding)
Oh, what have I done?
Children don't remember
bad birthdays, do they?
(sighs)
Good morning, honey.
Did you cry out all your angries?
I don't think so.
Oh, Lisa's still mad at me.
I'm still mad at you
for chopping up my skateboard with an axe.
I did it for the insurance money.
Huh!
Look, Lisa, I'm still trying
to get to know you.
-(horn honks)
-Who's your favorite Traveling Wilbury?
Is it Jeff Lynne?
Dad, you've had eight years
to get to know me.
It's too late.
(tires screech)
But I'm full of questions.
What's your favorite cigar size?
Is it Robusto? Is it?
LENNY: Gee, Homer...
you sure look sad.
Yeah.
At least you ain't aging
six years for every one
'cause of your cow heart.
Oh, my daughter hates me
because I don't know anything about her.
Ah. Well, whenever
I got to know something about a broad
I use this guy.
This detective is unbelievable.
He can learn more about a chick
by digging through one garbage can
than you could from years of intimacy.
He found out who was cobbling
shoes for me at night.
Turns out I have severe schizophrenia.
Well, if hiring this guy
will make Lisa like me again,
then I'll do it.
Can I get this beer to go?
Sure.
Maybe someday, I'llturn into a swan.
(sighs)
Ah, God.
(jazz theme plays)
(tires squeal)
(electrical buzzing)
(door squeaks)
Drunk Cop?
Is that you?
No. Look lower.
HOMER: Ooh! Pie.
What can I do for you?
My name is Homer Simpson
and I desperately need your help.
Let me guess. It's about a girl.
(gasps) How did you know?
It's always a dame.
Usually, with gams that don't quit...
till they get to the shoes,
and then they're only napping.
(chuckles)
Priceless.
I need you to find out
everything about my daughter
so she'll think I'm a good dad.
OK, I'll get a line on your kid.
I charge 50 bucks a day, plus expenses.
Anything to trick my daughter
into liking me.
Now, if you need to reach me
my e-mail is chunkylover53@aol.
"Chunky... lover... 53?"
It's one word.
One word.
Chunkylover53.
At AOL.
Dot com.
(jazz theme plays)
(camera shutter clicks)
(floor waxer whirring)
Hey, that's not your locker.
You know, you are the spitting image
of the Aberdeen Strangler.
Move along.
(whistling)
I need to see Lisa Simpson's
permanent record.
I'm afraid that
information is confidential.
These are some nice-looking
papers on your desk.
It would be a shame
if somebody shuffled them.
You wouldn't dare.
Oh, wouldn't I?
(scoffs) I could easily put them back
in their original order.
Oh, really?
(echoing scream) No!
You're late, Muntz.
Get bent, Shamus.
I got what you're looking for.
Nice... very nice.
Now give me back what's mine.
(sighs)
My picture with Snow White.
You know, she's just an actress.
Shut up!
Some of us prefer illusion to despair.
(horn honks)
Lisa Simpson is a girl at my school.
Yes, yes, you said that already.
What else do you know?
I once picked my nose till it bleeded.
(sighs) About Lisa!
Lisa Simpson is a girl at my school.
Someone's already worked this guy over.
(horn whistling)
Ah, the information I've been waiting for.
So far, so good.
(mumbling)
(gasps) Lisa's pet peeve is phonies?
I thought she loved them!
(jazz playing)
Huh?
Is that Miles Davis' Birth of the Cool?
You should know.
It is your favorite album.
So, you know one thing about me.
Big deal.
-(record scratching)
-HOMER: Wait, wait!
I thought you might like to go
to an animal rights protest today.
Well, maybe.
On the way home we could stop
and get your favorite treat--
ice...
cream.
What do we want?
ALL: The gradual phase-out
of animal testing
over the next three years!
When do we want it?
Over the next three years!
Uh, young lady,
why are you protesting today?
Because this lab
is cruelly testing consumer
products on animals.
Take a look for yourself.
They're making monkeys smoke cigarettes...
(exhales)
(contented sigh)
...and look at the way
they've slathered those pigs
with cosmetics!
So sad, yet so sexy, yet so delicious.
Mm...
Dad, today was so great.
The animal rights protest,
a visit to the Museum,
of Sadness and Oppression...
Well, we should get along.
I mean, after all, I am your...
father.
How'd you think of such
perfect things for us to do?
Did mom help you?
Mom? Don't you think I could
read the report by myself?
What report?
Uh--uh, well, "report" is a daddy word
that means "loves his daughter."
You read the "loves his
daughter" by yourself?
That's right, honey.
(door opens)
You did it!
Lisa thinks I'm the greatest.
I might even put you to work
on Bart and Maggie--
go super-dad on all their asses!
I believe there's still
the matter of my expenses.
Oh, yes. Well, let's take a look and see.
A thousand dollars?
How did you spend $1,000?
It's itemized.
A $40 steak?
Yeah, but if I'd eaten the whole thing
it would've been free.
You've been living like a king
on my dollar.
Super unleaded gas... silver bullets?
Early on I was working under the theory
that your daughter was a werewolf.
It didn't pan out.
I can't believe a man who agreed
to follow my daughter around for money
would turn out to be a dirtbag.
You better pay up, Simpson.
(grunting)
(whimpering)
You'll regret the day
you crossed Dexter Colt!
you went to the expensive coffee place!
(grunting)
♪ Color him father ♪
♪ I think I'll color him love ♪
♪ Color him love...♪
Breaking news at the Screaming
Monkey Research Labs
where hundreds of test animals
have been freed by unknown activists.
Chief Wiggum, do you have a statement?
Uh, yes. Yes, I do, Kent.
This is a horrible crime, one that...
(laughter)
Cut it out, Lou.
I... he's making funny faces.
Sorry, chief. One of these monkeys
has the same name as my ex-wife.
(laughs)
Chief, do you have any suspects
at this time?
Well, we do have several promising clues.
Ah, let's see... there's
a "Malibu Stacy" scrunchie,
a saxophone reed,
and a book report on The Secret Garden
by Lisa Simpson.
Well, what does this tell you, Chief?
Well, apparently, there's a secret garden
in all of us...
and that Lisa Simpson is guilty!
(all gasping)
I was framed!
You believe me, don't you, dad?
Of course, I do.
It's all my fault for refusing to pay--
(nervous laugh) ...pay attention to you.
My sweet little, father-loving
pile of forgiveness.
Yes!
(knocking)
Can Lisa come out with her hands up?
Chief Wiggum,
my daughter is innocent
until proven guilty.
(tires squeal)
Would an innocent person flee?
No, really. Tell me.
I--I honestly don't know.
Chief, no.
Even I knew that.
Yeah, yeah, I'm not... I'm not good.
(sirens wailing)
(tires screeching)
(sirens stop)
Heh, heh. They're trapped.
Oh, damn it!
Oh, I can't stop worrying
about Homer and Lisa.
Aw, Mom.
This will take your mind off them.
(grunts)
Oh, thank you, sweetie.
(humming)
(glass shattering)
NEWSCASTER: Police are looking
for a bald man in blue pants
and a fair-haired girl in a red lampshade.
Blackening our hair was a great idea, Dad.
I look just like a Powerpuff Girl.
I look just like Elvis.
(groans)
(car approaching)
(tires screeching)
Names, please?
Lady Penelope Ariel-Ponyweather.
Uh... Rock Strongo.
Your real name?
Uh... Lance Uppercut.
Thank you.
Sign here, Mr. Uppercut.
Let me just put on my glasses.
You're charging how much for a room?
(phone ringing)
Hello?
HOMER (phony voice):
Hello, this is a phone survey.
If the election were held today,
would you vote for A, the cops are there
or B, you're free to talk?
Uh, "A".
And I'd like to add
that Proposition "Hug Lisa for Me"
has my full support.
Oh, Marge, you're not getting it.
It's me, Homer. Simpson.
(chuckles nervously)
We got a location, Chief.
Good work, Lou.
We'll leave right after dinner.
Lisa, this is from your mom.
(grunts)
Ah...
Life on the lam is really hard
but at least it's with you, Dad.
I feel terrible
for putting you through this
after what a wonderful father you've been.
Oh... Lisa, I can't lie to you any longer.
This is all my fault.
I'm the worst dad in the world.
What? Why?
The man who framed you
is a crooked detective.
Who I hired.
Why did you do that?
To find out everything about you
so I'd seem like a good father.
How could you?
Well, all the childless drunks at Moe's
thought it was a great idea.
Let's just get some sleep.
All right, Simpsons, the jig is up!
We know you're in there!
HOMER: OK, I'm coming right out the door.
Damn it!
These windows are
so hard to squeeze through!
(Homer grunts)
Cheer up, honey.
We're living an all-natural existence,
the kind you like.
Ooh, a trash can.
We'll find breakfast in here.
I don't want to eat from the trash.
Ooh, a banana.
What the...?
It's full of cigarette butts.
So is this one.
They must've come from over there.
(circus calliope playing)
Those are the test animals.
The detective must've
sold them to the circus.
We'll just tell the police
and then I'm back to being
plain ol' Rock Strongo.
COLT: You're not telling nobody nothing.
Make one move and you'll get a bellyful
of The Flying Giuseppe.
How you doing?
Dexter Colt.
The man who framed my daughter.
You should've paid the expenses.
In retrospect, yes.
(gasping)
(loud explosion)
(grunting)
Ooh, I think that fixed my back.
(cracking) Oh... oh, no, no.
It's much worse.
(fretful moaning)
I'll just hide here.
(shrieks)
(electrical crackling)
(laughing) Now what are you going to do?
You can't shoot all of us.
-(gunshot)
-Damn it!
You know, Simpson,
from the moment you walked into my office
I had a feeling
I'd kill you in a hall of mirrors.
Dad, are you in here?
How did she find us?
Oh, Lisa has excellent hearing.
Once, when she was three
I was quietly sobbing in the closet,
and she found me.
Oh, Dad, you do remember
something about me.
Perhaps you also remember
this laser Bart gave me earlier.
(screams)
(grunts) I can't see!
How ironic.
Now he's blind
after a life of enjoying
being able to see.
Well, it wasn't easy, honey,
but I'm glad you love me again.
Yeah. But what's
going to happen to the animals?
Don't worry, honey.
I released them all into the wild.
-(monkeys chattering)
-(pigs squealing)
Cletus, if I find pig lipstick
on your collar again
I'm not going to let you
sleep in the sty no more.
Duly noted.
(theme music playing)
BART: Hey, Dad, will you
read me a bedtime story?
HOMER: Why, certainly, Son.
Just hand me that book you've got there.
(computerized voice) Unauthorized user.
-Access denied!
- (electrical zapping)
-(Homer yelling)
-(Bart laughing)
-(zapping)
-(yelling continues)
Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services