Ha, ha, I don't know, neighbor-inos.
I'm all for Halloween fun
but a seance sounds a little PG-13.
But this is your chance
to contact your late wife, Maude.
Well, I do miss the missus.
Maude Flanders, we the living beseech you
to appear.
BART (as Maude): Ned...
I'm back.
Give me a kiss.
(all screaming)
(in normal voice)
Chill out, dudes. It's me, Bart Simpson.
(whimpering)
What are you looking at?
(wailing)
(all screaming)
Maude. You still look as pretty
as the day I buried you.
(purrs)
Are you ready for tales
that will shatter your spine
and boil your blood?
-Well, duh.
-Then choke on these!
(laughing maniacally)
(Homer screaming)
Now to spend some quality time
away from my family.
(sighs)
I've got a list of things
for you to do today.
-My favorite is number three.
-Oh, I'd love to.
But someone made me too many pancakes
and now I have to sleep them off.
Oh, those were for the Church breakfast.
Were they now?
(grunts)
(groans)
Hammocks. Get your hammocks.
The hammock man. I'm glad
he's a little early today.
The price is $10.
But I must warn you,
this is no ordinary hammock.
Its webbing is a mesh of comfort and evil.
You had me at "comfort."
Mm-hmm. Hmm, Mr. Hammock,
say hello to Madam Ass.
(grunting)
(shouting)
What the... It made another me.
How cool is that?
(groans)
Hmm, no bellybutton.
Shuttle's in the hangar.
You wanna be my slave?
(moaning indistinctly)
Outstanding.
-Oh, uh... Mm-hmm.
-(electricity crackling)
Speed it up, ugly.
-(Homer clone screams)
-(thuds)
(Homer grunts)
Eh, he had a good run.
(grunting)
I'm gonna need help with this. Hmm.
(laughs)
(slurps)
Beer for me?
No, you've got chores to do.
Chores? Me need clone.
Clone? That's ridiculous.
Where am I supposed to find a...
Wait a minute.
(grunting)
Wow, four of me.
I think this could be a magic hammock.
And it just might be the answer
to my problems.
-Uh...
-MARGE: What do you think, Homer?
Does this make my hips look big?
(in monotone voice)
Outfit good, flatters butt.
Oh, aren't you a dear?
Then after World War II,
it got kind of quiet
till Superman challenged FDR
to a race around the world.
FDR beat him by a furlong.
Or so the comic books
would have you believe.
The truth lies somewhere in between...
(snoring)
(Homer grunts)
(grunts)
Me good dad.
Hmm. Does Dad seem
a little dumber than usual?
Me not notice.
Homie, you've been
such a sweetheart today.
Let's go upstairs and...
(whispers)
(chuckles)
(grunts)
-I'll take it from here, fake-o.
-Uh-uh.
-Uh-huh. Unh!
-Unh!
(in unison) Why you little... Aah!
Man, are we evenly matched.
Me concur.
(both gagging)
-(yells)
-(laughs)
It would take three clones
to beat the original Homer.
ALL: Hmm.
Huh, I mean four.
-ALL: Oh.
-Suckers.
(chattering)
MARGE: Kids, your father
made us breakfast.
BART AND LISA: Yay!
-Go, go, go.
-OK.
(kids munching)
Say, Homer, I was, uh...
I was wondering if I could borrow
that chainsaw you, uh, stole from me.
Yeah, but you have to leave a credit card.
-No problem. Discover OK?
-Ned.
OK, here's my Amex.
(grunts)
Mm-hm.
Homie, I must say you have the energy
of 20 men lately.
Twenty-three.
Now, today, I'm gonna mow the lawn,
do my taxes, shoot hoops with Bart
and girl it up with Lisa.
Aw.
-(yelps)
-(door slams)
(groaning)
Oh, I gotta get rid of these guys.
(tires squeal)
Now, before I abandon you
in this cornfield,
does anyone remember the way home?
I do.
-(fires)
-(body thuds)
Anybody else?
Come on.
OK, everyone out.
(all grunting)
Now to make sure this hammock
never troubles anyone again.
(grunts)
(tires screeching)
Ooh. Mm?
(groans)
(chattering)
Let's all go out for some frosty
chocolate milk shakes.
(all moaning)
Ah, look at that corn. Old Gil's hard work
is finally paying off.
(munching)
Well, at least I got my health.
Aw.
CLONES: Beer, beer, beer.
Beer, beer, beer.
-(cans ripping open)
-(clones gulping)
(clones babbling)
(pants unzipping)
(clones sighing)
Like comedy clubs in the late '80s,
these ravenous clones are everywhere.
They've destroyed every building in town
except Moe's Tavern, which is reporting
record business.
(chattering)
(gulping)
Now, uh, who's gonna be
picking up the tab?
ALL: Lenny.
Anything for Homers.
Dad, is there something
you'd like to tell us about this horde?
You'd think so, but no.
They look like you, they were rude
to Patty and Selma,
and the horde has been
describes very gassy.
Yeah, it's a good group.
Currently the, uh, Vietcong--
I mean, the, uh, Homers
are occupying these areas.
By tomorrow...
(all shuddering)
Good God, we're doomed.
No!
We're out of doughnuts.
That's it. I know exactly
what we should do.
Thank God.
And you said we shouldn't let little girls
in the war room.
Look, I was wrong, OK?
(all gasping)
ALL: Mm, doughnuts.
Want doughnut.
-Doughnut.
-Chocolate.
(all screaming)
ALL: D'oh! D'oh! D'oh!
HOMER CLONE: Son of a...
D'oh!
Thank you, General. That's a big relief.
The horde is almost dead.
There's still some writhing and twitching.
-But that should stop by morning.
-Good news.
Mm.
One handsome hubby is all I need.
(Marge gasps)
No bellybutton? You're a clone.
-Then the real homer...
-First over cliff.
(gasps)
My Homie's dead?
How will I go on?
You like back rub?
Oh, well.
(Crosby, Stills And Nash's
"Love The One You're With" playing)
♪ And if you can't be
With the one you love. honey ♪
♪ Love the one you're with ♪
(band harmonizing)
(thunder crashing)
(squeaks)
Goldie, you were more
than just a goldfish.
-You were a member of the family.
-Rest in peace, pal.
"William H. Bonney.
Gunned down July 14, 1881. Aged 21."
So young.
"I dream of a world without guns."
Don't we all, William?
♪ Lisa has a dead boyfriend ♪
He's not my dead boyfriend.
He is a dead boy
who happens to be my friend.
Mr. Bonney, I'm gonna
make your dream come true.
If not for guns,
poor William Bonney
might've become a doctor or a senator.
Or a frustrated novelist.
Ha, ha, sure.
The point is let's stop
the madness and ban guns now.
CROWD: Yeah!
Yee-haw! The girl's right.
I'm sorry. I can't live without passion.
Well, well, not so tough without your gun,
are you, Snake?
(groans)
Ow. I guess you are.
That's what I like
about this job, you learn stuff.
Twenty-eight, 29. There's one missing.
Not Mr. Blastie.
It's OK, boy. You'll be shooting
angels in heaven.
(sobbing)
Well, boys, now it's our turn.
Uh, this always made me
feel like a man, you know?
Now all I got is my enormous genitals.
Three cheers for a gun-free Springfield!
-Hip, hip...
-CROWD: Hooray!
-BONNEY: Hooray!
(thunder crashing)
Springfield's weapons of death
have been converted
into weapons of climbing and sliding.
-(giggling)
-(random firing)
The bumps tickle my bottom.
I proudly declare our town
utterly defenseless.
If only poor William Bonney
were here to see his dream come true.
Oh, but I am.
William Bonney?
Better known as Billy the Kid. (laughs)
(all gasping)
(gunfire)
Looks like the only guns left
are in my cold dead hands.
Now, I'd like you to meet
the Hole in the Ground Gang.
Frank and Jesse James.
(all gasping)
-The Sundance Kid.
-(all gasp)
What happened to Butch Cassidy?
"What happened to Butch Cassidy?"
We're not joined at the hip, you know.
And the most evil German of
all time, Kaiser Wilhelm.
CROWD: Huh?
He ain't no cowboy.
Sure I am.
Yippy, wippy, wippy.
OK, he's in.
Now, let's rob the bank,
give the money to the poor
then rob the poor and shoot the money.
(cheering)
-(speaking in German)
-(horses neighing)
(screaming and gunfire)
(grunts)
Play us some "pian-ee."
("Fur Elise" playing on piano)
(gunshot)
That's piano! I said, "pian-ee."
(playing ragtime tune)
You, play the "cell-ee."
You, sing a song about cattle rustling.
And you, sing one about,
uh, robbing banks.
♪ Calf's in the field
so you sneak up slow ♪
♪ Grab him by the tail and go, man, go ♪
♪ Break into the bank
and snatch that dough ♪
BOTH: ♪ Please don't hurt our family ♪
(cheering)
Marge, let me do a solo.
This could be my big break.
I very much doubt that, Homer.
These are horrible ghouls from the past.
Hey, so are the Grammy judges.
Ha-ha-ha, ugh!
Pardon the grabbing,
but I've perfected a device
that could save us all.
A time machine.
We can go back to the past
and save our guns.
Give me.
Uh, for flailing out loud,
I hope he doesn't do anything
to ruin the space-time
continuum. That's all...
Oh, dear.
Poor William Bonney might have
become a doctor or a senator.
(all gasping)
Hear me, people of the past.
Hey, everyone, that's us.
I come to deliver
a terrifying message of hope.
Grab your guns and follow me.
-Yeah!
-All right!
(chattering)
Dad, what are you doing?
Ooh, how to explain this to a child? Hmm.
Future Daddy needs
to double kill these corpses
so they won't come back
as zombies and... Get him!
(shouting)
(screaming)
(corpses grunting)
(crowd cheering)
Another tragedy prevented by gun violence.
I guess guns really are the answer.
Hear me, people of Springfield.
I come from yet another distant future
where gun violence has destroyed
the very Earth itself.
What is this, open mike night?
Hah! Now to get me some caveman hookers.
Tell me again why we're spending
our vacation on the Island of Lost Souls.
Hey, what could be more fun than an island
shaped like a big smiley face?
Welcome to my island.
Dr. Hibbert? But we heard you'd gone mad.
Yes, completely mad.
About providing topnotch vacation values.
(laughs)
Willie, help them with their bags.
(groans)
-(growls)
-(Simpsons gasp)
Now, he may try to slobber on your crotch.
Heh! I've been around Scotsmen.
(screams)
(whimpers)
Homer, someone's in trouble.
Hey, I'm on vacation.
Dr. Hibbert, this is a topnotch resort.
Can you recommend some activities?
Well, one activity you might enjoy
is not asking questions.
(laughs)
But man's inquisitive nature
is what separates us from the animals.
And why must we be separated, dammit?
Think what Shakespeare
might've accomplished
if he'd had the eyes of an eagle
or could spray stink on his critics.
Now, who'd like some turkey?
It's a lovely nerd...
(laughs) I mean "bird."
(screams)
No! Wait a minute now.
Guess what, I'm dying, ha, ha...
...with the basting and the butterballing
and the chestnut stuffing in my pupik.
Gobble, gobble, gobble. Death.
Homie, something very creepy
is going on here.
You mean they're gonna try
to sell us timeshares?
I think I'm going to do
a little sleuthing.
Bring back some ice.
(people shouting nearby)
"House of pain." This must be where
you pay the bill.
(laughs)
Why am I always so funny
when no one's around?
(groaning)
Oh, I'm around.
(Marge shouting and growling)
(purrs)
Unh. What's up, honey?
Want a little loving?
(purrs)
Woo-hoo, quite a tiger there.
Easy, easy. Ha, ha,
I guess it has been a while.
OK, that hurts more than it tickles.
(Marge purring)
Quiet, youse.
-(thuds)
-(Marge yelps)
Isn't vacation sex always the best?
(growls in agreement)
Marge, you were like a wild beast.
So voracious and prowly.
And I've never seen you
use your tail like that.
(bird chirps)
(growls)
What the... Oh, my God.
She's become a monster.
Which I have to admit, I sort of suspected
during the sex.
(groans)
Gotta find a way to change Marge back.
And replace the M&M'S I took
from the minibar.
NED: Hey, Homer.
Flanders.
Oh, a perfect vacation ruined.
Hate to be a needy Neddy,
but could you do me a favor?
-Hmm.
-Milk me.
Uh, I really don't wanna do that, Ned.
Oh, come on, Homer. All I'm asking
is for you to yank my teats
-and harvest my milk.
-Ugh, fine.
Ooh, that's nice.
You're actually quite
gentle when you wanna be.
You know, you're not helping.
♪ In the jungle the jungle,
the creepy jungle ♪
♪ Homer rides a freak ♪
Shh. Hey.
(indistinct chattering)
Huh! What's that?
(grunts)
(squeaks)
I'm a dog.
(blows horn)
Hear me, accursed brethren.
I understand that some of you
are still wearing tattered pants.
Please, throw them on the bonfire
and embrace your animal essence.
OK, but I'm keeping the tattered vest.
I still have my dignity.
Hey, slops.
Ooh, a toenail. Ha, ha.
I can't believe it.
Hibbert's turned you all
into human guinea pigs.
We prefer "Italian-American pigs."
Hey, Dad, check it out.
"Eat my shorts"? Why, you little...
Maggie.
Lisa. Ugh!
We were just playing.
What game?
Let's Eat Maggie.
(grunts)
Manimals, inverta-broads.
You must fight back against
the one who did this to you.
Yar, the half-man, half-gorilla
speaks the truth.
(all grunt in agreement)
(laughing)
Now, I admit I made a few mistakes,
but all in the name of progress.
Hear, hear.
-It's Mr. Burns.
-With a fox attitude.
Think about it, my hideous children.
Aren't you better off now
than you were as humans?
Me gusto pollen.
Disco Shrew can still boogaloo.
(disco music playing)
(all groan in disgust)
You guys are nuts.
All you can do is eat and sleep
and mate, and roll around
in your own filth
and mate and eat-- Where do I sign up?
(bird chirps)
So how do you like being a walrus, Dad?
It's great. I haven't been
this skinny since high school.
Homie, someone owes me a back scratch.
(groans in pleasure)
Look at that island
shaped like our number four.
Makes you think.
(theme music playing
in tune of space music)
-(indistinct screeching)
-(organ music playing)
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services