(theme music playing)
CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell rings)
(whistle blows)
(beeps)
(playing the blues)
(tires screeching)
D'oh! (screams)
Hello, I'm Kent Brockman,
and this is Eye on Springfield.
(flashy pop music playing)
I'm here with actor Rainier Wolfcastle,
who, surprisingly,
has filed for bankruptcy.
Rainier, what went wrong?
Three divorces in three months.
What can I say, Kent?
I'm a romantic.
But this personal tragedy translates
into a good, old-fashioned
bankruptcy sale.
Yeah, everything must go.
Even the painting of my Nana.
This was done on her wedding day,
or should I say... deading day?
How the mighty have fallen...
into my price range!
I wanna go there.
Dad, we are there.
Whoo-hoo!
Now, Rainier, I really
don't think it's right
to sell these Playdude centerfolds.
(girls chuckling)
Zip it, Holy Joe.
Are you taking us to another mansion?
Uh... yeah.
Uh, Miss September, I think
-you're gonna have to get in the trunk.
-Oh.
Whoa, a sword cane.
Everything here is sword.
Sword baseball bat.
Sword rifle.
Sword pineapple.
Sword sword sharpener.
Sword pie. It's...
Hey, what happened to the sword pie?
What do I do now?
Hey, look, a cyborg hand.
This could really come in useful.
Well, well, look who's gone Hollywood.
Whoo... um... eh...
Do you need some assistance
picking over the tattered
remains of my life?
No, I'm good.
Hey, your early porno movies.
Holy... Are any of these hetero?
What's there is there.
You got any junk that'll go up
in value after you die?
Right this way.
My first weight set.
(gasps)
The weights that changed you
from a Bavarian cream puff
to a mass of twitchy muscles?
(chuckling)
They know you are talking about them.
I'll take it.
Who's up for coconut oil?
There's no way all this junk
is going to fit in that car.
Now, don't worry.
This is what all those hours
of playing Tetris were for.
(Tetris 8-bit music plays)
No!
Perfect.
But there's no room for you.
D'oh!
(game-over tones)
Do you think you could
give me a lift home?
Sure, I'll carry you
in this giant Snuggli.
I used it to carry Rob Schneider
in the movie My Baby is an Ugly Man.
Mm? Ooh.
(grunts)
(yawns)
Your heartbeat is so soothing.
Shh.
Time for sleep, little fatso.
Aw!
Ew! Mom!
I think Maggie fudged her Huggies.
Bart, don't say it like that.
You'll hurt her feelings.
(sniffing)
(gagging) Geez Louise!
How did you turn
cinnamon applesauce into that?
Don't try to pin this on me, sister.
MARGE: Sorry. Emergency.
(grunting)
Hello, Mrs. Homer.
Apu, where is your bathroom?
The bathroom is not for customers.
Please use the crackhouse
across the street.
Oh! That is the most pungent thing
I have ever smelled, and I am from India.
All right, all right,
but speak of this to no one.
Don't worry, that sign is just a ruse--
like all "high voltage" signs.
Hmm...
There's a happy baby, aren't you?
(laughing happily)
Gimme your purse.
Oh, God. Oh, God, oh, God.
-Shut up.
-(both gasp)
-That's not a purse. It's a diaper bag.
-What?
It looks like a purse.
-That's why I bought it but it's really--
-Shut up!
(whimpers)
Fine. I'll just take this!
(gasps)
Come on, Mom. Let's go.
Mom?
-Are you OK?
-(Marge crying)
It's all my fault my wife got mugged.
There you have it, boys. Case closed.
Look, this really made me feel vulnerable.
I want to know how soon you think
you'll catch this guy.
Don't worry, Marge.
I swear to you I'll put my best man on it.
BOTH: Mm?
Oh, boy, is this awkward.
Wait, Marge.
I don't want you to leave
the house without this.
Emergency whistle,
pepper spray, and this map
of the most vulnerable parts
of a man's body.
Why is it Ned Flanders?
Oh, like I'm going to kick
Chief Wiggum in the groin.
OK, Marge, you can do this.
You've done it a thousand times before.
-Hi, Mrs. Simpson.
-Aah!
(coughs)
Oh, no! I pepper sprayed Ralph.
(coughs): Even my boogers are spicy.
Sorry!
Let's go home.
There's nothing dangerous there
except for the electrical wiring.
(breathing heavily)
Mom, you didn't get the milk.
And you parked on top of the mailman.
It's OK. All part of the job.
Can you believe I get paid
to wear short pants?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'll come right out and help you.
(grunts)
I gave your necklace
to my cheap girlfriend.
I just throw it in a drawer at night.
(cackles)
No! It'll tangle!
Sorry, I can't go outside.
I'll call for help.
No hurry, I got plenty to read.
Whoo, Twilight Zone magazine.
Oh, no, my glasses are broken.
(Twilight Zone theme plays)
Marge, I'm afraid
you've developed agoraphobia--
A fear of leaving the home.
I recommend watching this
Lifetime Channel movie.
It's called, The Woman
Who Died In Her Home.
(chuckles)
Oh, my God.
Isn't there anything I can do?
Marge, I suggest
you slowly desensitize yourself
to the fear of going outside.
Create controlled situations
where you can leave the house
without pain or panic.
What if I can't feel
comfortable outside again?
Then I hope you like
throwing dinner parties.
I do.
No one wants to eat dinner
at a crazy lady's house.
Get real.
LISA: Don't worry, Mom.
This first time, we'll only take
a few steps outside.
All right, just to the mailbox and back.
Now, Dr. Hibbert said
to use a number from one to ten
to describe how anxious you are.
Two... three... two.
Don't worry, everything is fine.
-What the hell is that?
-Eight.
-Dad, it's just a bug.
-Two.
It's not just a bug,
it's the queen of something!
Ten, ten, ten, ten.
Don't worry, I'll set fire to the hive.
Twelve. Fifteen!
-(bees buzzing)
-703!
Run!
Oh, my goodness.
It looks just like the Kwik-E-Mart.
Yep, but you're still safe at home.
After a few practice trips here,
the real Kwik-E-Mart
will be a piece of cake.
-Now, Bart will play Apu.
-Mm-hmm.
I'm a magazine rack.
Look, I'm the first to admit it.
I don't write good parts for women.
I'm a robber!
(grunts)
(screams) Help!
All this does is shoot bubbles.
(yells)
Silly String!
Kids, I'll go find your mother.
Dad, we're canceling the rest of the play.
What play?
What the hell's he talking about?
-Marge?
-I'm going to sleep down here tonight.
Listen, kids.
Your mom is going to be living
in the basement,
but with our love, she'll get better soon.
What if she doesn't?
Then we'll have to smoke her out.
And may the peace of God
be with you. Amen.
-MARGE: Amen. Over.
-(static)
Breaker, breaker, Bartman to shut-in.
The big guy's asleep. Please advise. Over.
Whack him with the hymnal. Over.
-I'll roger that big time.
-D'oh!
HOMER: Why, you little...
(chuckles) Oh, hi, Jesus.
I was just...
(Homer munching)
Wow, honey, eating dinner
downstairs is great.
Isn't it, kids?
The air hockey table
makes passing the carrots a breeze.
Bart, eat your spinach.
No way.
Yes way.
(both grunting)
Stop it, please.
I'm trying to eat.
And all those feet going by the window
are really creeping me out.
It's like we're at Cheers.
I loved that show
because you always knew it
was only a half hour till Wings.
Then you could just sleep till Monday.
BOTH: Bye, Mom.
MARGE: I'm sending the cat up
with your lunches.
(grunted meows)
(meowing)
Good-bye, kids.
(sighs) What to do now?
Too crazy to go outside,
not crazy enough
to have imaginary friends.
Why did Homer buy those?
No one's ever going to use them.
Hmm.
-(grunts) MAN ON TV: And three...
and four...
and five eggs.
Ladies, feel that burn.
If you don't, the oven's not on.
MARGE: Ten...
Eleven...
Twelve...!
I can bench twice as
much as when I started.
And look at my abs.
BOTH: Mom!
Ooh-woo-woo-woo!
I'm married to Joey Heatherton.
Ooh, you know what would
zest up this Hollandaise?
A lemon.
Dad, do you plan to get in shape?
No, actually, I'm going
to eat twice as much.
Excellent.
Uh, guys?
Mom just left the basement.
(all gasp)
(gasps) She's in the backyard.
I got all the way out to the tree
before I realized I'd left the house.
(grunts)
(gasps) I'm stronger than I've ever been.
I don't have to go back inside.
I'm not afraid.
-All right, Mom!
-Yay, Mom!
Whoo-hoo!
I'm not afraid!
Ned! I'm not afraid!
Well, aren't you a super-duper recouper.
Grampa!
I'm not afraid!
Then you're not paying
close enough attention.
(gasps) You!
What you been up to? Living in fear?
Not anymore.
(grunting)
Ow-ow-ow!
(glass shatters)
(grunts)
You've just been Marge-inalized.
(cheering)
Marge, that was amazing.
It's like I'm married to Shaft.
Hey, Chief, I think
that's the guy who mugged her.
Yep, looks like
she caught her own criminal...
Unlike the rest of you lazybones.
You're not going to find those criminals
looking at your feet, people.
(theme from Rocky plays)
(metal clinking)
WOMAN: Marge Simpson?
It's Ruth.
Ruth Powers.
Ruth Powers? My old neighbor?
Oh, my goodness, look at you!
I got this body in prison.
I was Miss Mexican Mafia
three years in a row.
Wow!
(seagulls crying)
You know, another four inches
on your neck,
and you'd look pretty hot.
Ever thought of competing?
I don't have those kind of muscles.
Well, you could, if you use these.
Steroids?
I can't take drugs.
I have so many anti-drug bumper stickers,
I'd be making a liar out of my tailgate.
Steroids aren't drugs.
They occur naturally in the body,
like sweat, or tumors.
But aren't there side effects?
Yes, their main side effect is greatness.
But if you'd rather be weak
and helpless...
No, no.
(Popeye the Sailor Man theme plays)
I feel good, with no repercussions.
(humming)
A little of this, a little of that.
Bulkenoids for my lats,
mesomax for my delts,
and estrogen blockers
for that minty taste.
(gulping)
Whoa!
(horn beeps)
Hurry up, kids. You'll miss the bus.
(hollering)
(grunts)
Not so fast, busboy.
Man! What am I smoking?
Oh, yeah. Pot.
BART AND LISA: Thanks, mom.
Bye, kids.
Bye-bye.
Haw-haw! Your mom changed!
Hey, hot stuff, I've got
a competition tomorrow.
I could use a good-luck snuggle.
I'd rather talk about our feelings.
I feel that illegal
performance-enhancing drugs
are too common these days.
-Rebuttal?
-(grunts)
Let's do it.
Oh, uh... Uh, listen, my bulky flower,
I-I have an early day...
I wasn't asking.
(whimpering)
Morning, kids. I made your lunches.
They're on the table.
Huh?
Why didn't Mom make our lunch?
Your mom has a lot of stuff to shave.
Ow. Ow.
ANNOUNCER (over P.A.):
Now, let's meet the ladies
who our doctors assure us are women...
the Iron Maidens.
Ay caramba!
I'm off women forever.
(grunts)
(gruff voice) Support the arts!
(all cheering)
This is the cheapest vacation
you've ever taken me on.
♪ The man who shot Liberty Valance ♪
♪ He shot Liberty Valance ♪
♪ He was the bravest of them all ♪
Nice lady.
In second place...
Marge Simpson.
Second place?
Oh, man, this'll just encourage her.
I'm tired of her
criticizing my saggy glutes.
Quiet. Her muscular ears can hear us.
(grunts)
So then, I pop my delts, clench and bam!
Not a dry eye in the house.
Oh, I'm so proud of you, honey.
You bulked up, but managed
to keep your femininity.
And that's why I didn't win.
Sorry, sir, sorry.
Starting tomorrow,
I'm going to up my glyco-load,
use a denser ripping gel...
Denser?
Damn straight!
I didn't sacrifice
my period for second place.
(chuckles)
I hear that!
Uh, listen, Marge.
Um... how can I put this delicately?
I don't got enough booze in this place
to make you look good.
(grunts) Ya!
Maybe death will stop your yammering, huh?
Marge, easy...
Ya! (yells)
(all gasp)
Everyone, pile on Homer's wife.
(grunting)
(song on radio)
♪ Love is a battlefield... ♪
(grunting)
♪ At last... ♪
♪ Relax, don't do it ♪
MAN: Disco Stu should have Disco Ducked.
(Homer whistling)
(classical music playing)
(all grunt)
(whimpering and crying)
(siren blaring)
Marge?
Somewhere in that sea of bull hormones
is the sweet, wonderful girl I married.
The woman who instead of swatting a fly
would give it a bath
and sent it on its way.
I'd sure like to go home
and have Jiffy Pop with her.
Oh, my gosh!
You're right.
Steroids have turned me
into everything I hate.
Let's go home, sweetie.
Club soda will get that blood out.
(groans)
Well, there's only one way
to recoup my losses.
Whoa, Moe, wait a minute.
Don't you have to buy insurance first?
Oh, crap.
(gasps)
(grunts)
You know, I really do miss being a lady.
And I miss being
your knight in flabby armor.
Oh, Homie.
(giggling)
HOMER: Ready for a real workout, Marge?
MARGE: Mm-hmm.
Good! Can you wax the car?
HOMER: Ow! Ow! Ow!
I'm kidding! I'm kidding!
(theme from Rocky playing)
(theme song playing)
Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services