CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(honking horn)
D'oh! (screams)
(tires screeching)
( Get Smart opening theme playing)
(grunts)
( The Simpsons theme resumes)
MAN: Welcome back to Animal Survivor.
(chimpanzee screeching)
OK, tribes, it's been a rough week.
Rhino, you lost the tribe's
fishing equipment.
(groaning)
And we saw a dramatic collapse
in the lion-gazelle alliance.
(roaring)
Oh, I hate reality shows.
A year ago, you said they were
the greatest thing
that ever happened to us.
I've grown, you haven't.
-(remote clicking)
-(applause)
MAN: And now,
we're back to Touch the Stove.
So Kevin, I hear you collect
amusing postcards.
Uh, yeah. It all started when...
(sizzling) Touch the stove!
(screaming)
I can't take any more of these shows.
If I wanted reality,
I'd finally have this lump looked at.
(squeaking rhythmically)
Networks love reality shows
because they don't have to pay
writers or actors.
Stupid writers and actors.
Priced yourselves right out
of the business.
Nice going, geniuses.
Hey, let's get one of those
home satellite dishes.
Then we can stop suckling
on the six-network teat.
Get back, honky cat.
Those systems are too expensive.
Marge, we can't pinch pennies
on the machine that's going
to be raising our children.
Come on, kids.
Daddy knows a way to get the money
with no risk.
(fanfare)
MAN (on P.A.): And the winner
by a nose is "No Risk."
Whoo-hoo!
(car honking)
OK, now, all we have to do
is install your satellite dish.
Can you be home from
8:00 a.m. Monday morning
through June?
No problem.
Hey, Flanders, check out
my new satellite dish.
(whistles)
Boy, that's Jim Dandy roof candy.
I'd love to come over some time
and watch that Church Channel.
I bet you would.
Oh, you'd win that bet.
Seems like I'm spending all my money
on religious pay-per-view.
Or as I like to call it, "pray-per-view."
Damn your sparkling wordplay!
And bless your humble home.
(frustrated grunting)
Oh, it's red wire to red wire.
(sputters lips)
What idiot dreamed that up?
And the Lord said,
"Let there be crap."
(clicks)
("Blue Danube" playing)
(monkeys chattering)
(music continues)
(wistful moaning)
(slurping)
...and thereby reducing
the number of states to 49.
Cool. It's the NBC news feed.
Mmm... feed.
You get to see what they do
during commercial breaks.
We'll be right back with a special report
on soccer moms who hate soccer.
MAN: Clear!
Oh, Lord, I'm so fat.
(gagging)
(retching)
Hey, Lis, want to try some satellite TV?
We've got Japanese Friends.
(lively music playing)
(with Japanese accent)
Do you like my new shirt?
It says "Reggae Hairstyle Rock N' Roll."
Could I be more Japanese?
You are the Emperor of Last Year.
Your comeback shames me.
How about the Clock Channel?
MAN: Coming up on the Clock
Channel... 6:00.
Wait a minute, I saw this one.
Bart, I have to study
for the Elementary School
Achievement Test.
And so do you.
Hey, I don't have to study on the weekend.
It's Wednesday night!
Kids, kids, you're both right.
-(moans)
-(growls)
MAN: We're back with Who Wants to Marry
an Internet Billionaire?
Uh, no, millionaire.
Well, now he's broke.
(swanky music playing)
(paper crinkling)
(munching loudly)
(both groaning)
Why don't you turn off the TV
and join us for dessert?
I made a pie.
Put pie here.
(sighs heavily)
(gulping, munching)
Would you like some ice cream with that?
Me not pig.
-(Homer snoring)
-MAN: We now return
to Robo Trumble.
Oh, I'm sorry. I mean Robot Rumble.
(robots grunting, metal clanking)
(mechanical voice)
Why are fighting each other?
Together, we can defeat
the humans and rule the Earth.
(mechanical voice) I agree.
(wheels whirring)
(crowd gasping)
-(saw grinding)
-Aah!
Sucker!
(chuckling)
Homicidal robots... so like us.
(snoring)
Bart, the test is in two hours
and you haven't slept in a fortnight.
What's a fortnight?
You should know. It's on the test.
-(grunting)
-(material suctioning)
MRS. KRABAPPEL: No pressure, children
but these test results will follow you
for the rest of your life
and beyond the grave.
BART: This test is boring.
What else is on?
(electrical zapping)
(retching)
(chuckling maniacally)
(zapping)
(lively music playing)
It's finally happened, Bart.
You've lost your mind.
(dramatic intro playing)
(all singing in Hebrew)
(laughing happily)
SKINNER (in English):
Now let's raise the roof
for the bland informative rap
of M.C. Safety
and the Caution Crew.
Yo, yo, yo. Y'all feeling cautious?
♪ I say a cross, walk, a crossity walk ♪
♪ And you don't stop crossin'
till you're on the next block ♪
♪ First you look both ways
then you walk, not run ♪
♪ Obeying safety rules is acceptable fun ♪
Break it down now.
♪ Just walk, don't run ♪
♪ Drink Juice, yum-yum. ♪
(chuckling)
Watch out, Beatles.
Now, I have one more important
announcement to share with you.
Would Lisa Simpson join me on stage?
Huh?
Lisa, because of your outstanding score
on yesterday's big test,
you're being immediately moved up to...
the third grade!
(cheering and applause)
She's not so great!
She got diarrhea when we went
to Carlsbad Caverns!
(laughter)
(gasps) Oh!
(laughter continues)
OK, Bart, since you like attention so much
I have a second announcement.
(murmuring)
I was going to tell you this privately,
but because of your incredibly
low test score,
we're sending you back to third grade.
(laughing)
The... wh... eh... Huh?
What? I've got to be
in the same class as her?
in the same class as him?
Hmm?
They're going to be in
the same class as each other?
(changes channel)
(gasps) An old army buddy
is visiting Mannix?
Class, meet our newest third graders--
Lisa and Bart Simpson.
Lisa comes to us from Miss Hoover...
(gulping)
...while Bart was taught
by Mrs. Krabappel.
(coughing) Slut!
ALL: Hi, Bart and Lisa.
A rooster sits on a roof, facing north.
It lays an egg.
Which way does it roll?
OK, the sun rises in the east
so the rooster
would probably want to lay it
on the cool side...
Roosters don't lay eggs.
They're boys.
Very good, Bart.
Mm-hmm.
Lisa, I want you to stick close
to your big brother
until you catch up.
(scraping)
-(loud clang)
-(appalled gasp)
Ha-ha.
Young man, you're not in this class.
What are you doing here?
Laughing at jerks.
"Quiet nerds burp only near school."
Bart, I'm doing my geography homework.
I know. That's how you remember
the four original provinces of Canada.
"Quebec, New Brunswick,
Ontario, Nova Scotia--
Quiet nerds burp only near school."
And here's how you remember
the principal exports:
"Dogs eat barf solely
on Wednesday, Mabel."
Stop. I want to learn on my own!
Canada's Governors General,
"Clowns love haircuts,
so should Lee Marvin's valet."
Get out!
(creaking)
McCONNELL: Here are your math tests.
Morgan, Dakota, Ashley,
Dakota, Tyler, Tyler, Lisa...
What's this weird mark next to my "A"?
That's an A-minus.
M-Minus?
Nice work, Bart.
An "A"?
Copacetic.
You did better than me?
Ah, I took this test last year.
The answer key never changes.
"B-C-B-C-A-A-B-B-C-C-D- False-False-True
William Jennings Bryan."
That's cheating!
Bart cheated!
Young lady, in the third grade,
we don't care for tattletales.
Oh...
And we don't care for moaners, either.
(crying)
Sobbing only pushes Bart's grade higher.
(pen squeaking)
(sobbing)
Pukers in back.
Kids, look what I got you
for your third-grade field trip,
matching fanny packs!
Now your fannies match.
(both groan)
(both grunting)
-Hey, get away from me. Get...!
-Out... ow, oh!
-Quit it!
-Ow, let go!
-Ow!
-Stop!
You'll crush your juice boxes!
(both moan)
(both groaning angrily)
All right, everybody choose
a buddy for the field trip.
I'll take Kyle!
I'll take Ashley!
Saying your buddy's name
out loud is a security risk.
I'll just put you two together.
(both moaning)
(song playing) ♪ There's a swingin' town
I know called... ♪
♪ Capital City... ♪
Punch buggy red! (grunts)
Ow! You are such an immature...
Punch buggy white!
Ow!
Stop fighting.
He started it.
He did Punch Buggy first.
What's "Punch Buggy"?
When you see a Volkswagen Bug
you punch somebody and yell the color.
(murmuring)
(all gasping)
-BOY: Punch Buggy blue!
-(thud) Ow!
-GIRL: Punch Buggy green!
-BOY: Punch Buggy taupe!
-(thud) Ow!
-(blows landing, crying)
-GIRL: That really hurt!
OTTO: Two for flinching!
(two blows land)
(children moaning)
Now, as we cross the street,
I want you to hold hands with your buddy.
(both moan)
(vehicle approaching)
(tires screech)
Hey, dude, who's your girlfriend?
(laughter)
Did you see his face?
(tires screech)
What happened, dude?
Did your girlfriend dump you?
(laughter)
(goofy honk)
(both moan)
Now children, if you look up
at the capitol dome,
you'll see a mural of our state bird,
the Pot-bellied Sparrow
eating our state pasta, bow-tie.
(children exclaiming)
Order, order, order.
The chair recognizes
the esteemed representative
from Capital City...
BART: The Capital City Goofball?
That's right.
To win, he spent $80 million
from his own pocket.
Mr. Speaker, the time has come
to redesign our state flag.
This confederate symbol
is an embarrassment.
Particularly as we are a northern state.
(crowd murmuring)
This lively debate has given me an idea.
Tonight, each buddy team
is going to design
a new state flag.
Homework on a field trip?
What have you been huffing?
Well, Bart's being his usual jerky self
but, Mom, I'm really excited
about this new flag design.
Oh, and the hotel gives you
a free USA Today
outside your room.
No, I'm sure it's free.
OK, I won't touch it.
Well, make sure you don't.
And try not to let your brother
get under your skin, honey.
Believe me, he doesn't.
His act is getting old fast.
He think he's really cool...
but frankly, the other kids
are starting to wake up
and smell the cooties.
One last sunbeam... and we're done.
"To Fraternal Love."
When I get through with that flag,
it's gonna be a Bart Mangled Banner.
("Pomp and Circumstance" playing)
So, I understand you children
have some state flags for me.
Who would like to go first?
We would, Governor Bailey!
Team Simpson!
I spearheaded this one.
I'll just unfurl this...
(horrified scream)
(all gasp)
That was my worst unfurling ever!
Lisa, how could you?
The governor is crying.
(sobbing)
(moans)
Ha-ha!
You weren't on this field trip.
How did you get here?
Biked.
Bart, I am so mad at you!
(laughs) You should have seen
the look on your face.
It was something like this.
(laughing)
(growls)
(both grunting)
(bubbling)
(groaning)
(horn honking)
-Huh?
-(gasps) The bus!
OK, children, before we leave
is anyone missing their buddy?
ALL: No.
Ah, the buddy system. Foolproof.
Floor it, Otto.
(gears grind)
LISA: Wait, wait!
(both panting)
Ha, ha.
(sing-song voice) They left without you
They left without you, too, you idiot.
Well, if I'm such an idiot,
how come I'm the smartest kid
in the third grade?
Because you've already done it once.
You've lost me.
Oh, forget it.
Hey, how do we get back?
No problem. We'll just circle around
like those kids
in The Blair Witch Project.
(panting) I must be getting close.
I recognize that girl!
Oh, Bart, I think we're lost.
I used to be lost...
until a friend turned me on to a book,
a book that changed my life.
It's called Lisa is Stupid.
You die now!
(gagging) Whoa!
Hey!
(laughing)
(teacher sobbing)
They're gone.
I don't know what happened.
If the buddy system can fail,
I don't know what to believe in.
There, there, Audrey.
It's happened to all of us.
Willie, we have two more
names for the wall.
(lone bugle plays mournfully)
(sniffling)
Ach! Why is it always the kids
with the long names?
(chugging)
(doorbell rings)
Hello, Principal Skinner.
A parent who waives
her right to sue says "What?"
What?
-Got it.
-Hey, you can't fool us.
We're from the "Learn to Fart" state.
(exhales)
Bart and Lisa are lost in Capital City
and presumed crying.
(gasps)
My poor babies!
I'm so sorry.
Lisa's a very special little girl,
and we'll spare no expense in finding her.
Well, what about Bart?
We're looking.
But in the meantime
the class clown pro-tem
will take his place.
Cowabunga!
(wind blowing)
(animal noises)
(Lisa shivering)
-You cold?
-What do you care?
(unzipping)
-Here.
-Thanks.
Where'd you get...
Oh.
Bart, you're my big brother.
You should act like it more often.
You know, protect me
from the bad things in the world.
Well, as far as nerdy little sisters go,
you're the coolest.
Thanks, Bart.
And I'm sorry I sabotaged your flag.
I'm sorry I got us lost out here.
Oh, and I'm sorry
I sawed the heads off
your Malibu Stacey dolls.
OK, you go.
I don't think I've done anything else.
OK, I'll go again.
Remember when your bike
was mangled by "gypsies"?
Yes...
(chuckles) Yeah, funny story,
One day, I was really bored
and Dad had left his steamroller idling
in the driveway...
This is where the kids were last seen.
(gasps)
The plastic casing from the tip
of Bart's shoelace!
A mother knows.
Well, he's not going
to get very far without that.
Bart, is that you?
MAN: No.
(rifles cocking)
-(both gasp)
-Say your prayers!
Oh, Lord, please strike
these mountain folk dead.
Bart!
Listen, we're really sorry.
We got lost on a field trip
from Springfield Elementary.
(sputters) Lost on a field trip?
Heck, why didn't you say so?
That's how Grandpappy wound up
in these parts.
They was taking us to Capital City to
see The Nutcracker.
And I wandered away from the group...
I married a bear
and I started up a family.
I told you, I ain't a bear.
(laughs) Rar, rar, rar.
No one understands you, She-Bear!
(laughs)
(car rattling)
Thanks for driving us back to town.
No problem. We were going there anyway
to pick up the new Spy magazine.
I'm sorry.
They don't publish that anymore.
The world I grewed up in is gone.
(kissing)
Oh, my special little guys!
You're OK! You're OK!
(kissing)
And, Maggie, you no longer have
to live with the burden
of replacing Bart and Lisa.
Well, if this episode
has taught us anything,
it's that nothing works better
than the status quo.
Bart, you're promoted
back to the fourth grade.
Yay!
And Lisa, you have a choice--
you may continue to be
challenged in third grade
or return to second grade
and be merely a big fish in a small pond.
Big fish! Big fish!
ALL: Aw...
The status quo.
The status quo?
Ay carumba!
That's just sad.
(closing theme music)
Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services