CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
Now, the topic
for your research paper
will be World War I.
Was that the war
with Hitler or Merlin?
Oh, you idiot.
Merlin was in Vietnam.
Instead of writing a report,
can I do a dance?
(singing a tune)
(grunts)
Sorry.
May I type my report?
It'll be easier
on teacher's eyes.
Yes. In fact, why doesn't
everyone type their paper?
Great idea, Martin.
Can the paper
be ten pages minimum?
Well, I was going
to say five, but OK.
Thanks again, Martin.
Martin?
He's gone now.
But you got
to admire his spirit.
All right, Seymour,
I'm ready for our romantic
apple-picking trip.
Yes, about that.
Mother's neck wattle
got caught in a zipper.
I've, uh... got a long night
of boo-boo kissing ahead of me,
but don't worry, I got you these
store-bought apples instead.
The apples weren't the point.
(chuckling)
Then why were
we going apple picking?
(sighing)
BART: OK...
time to start this paper.
(sighs)
World War I.
W.W.I.
Eh, that's a good start.
Time to watch wrestling.
ANNOUNCER: I can't believe it.
(grunting)
Uncle Slam has defeated
Osama Bin Rotten. Uh-oh!
Here come Secretary of Hate,
Colin Kapow!
He's dropping sanctions...
by which I mean anvils.
(grunting)
(crowd cheering on TV)
(deep breath)
OK, got to focus, got to focus.
Got to look at that bird.
Got to focus.
(clock ticking)
MAN: Damn it.
Why did I pay for 100 Xeroxes
when I only wanted one?
Well, I guess someone else
will use the other 99.
Oh...
Prank or study? Prank or study?
What should I do, Lord?
Give me a sign.
(chuckling)
(copy machine whirring)
(organ playing)
MAN: Now, if everyone would
open your prayer books...
(screaming)
(laughing)
Well, boys, good thing
we brought the eye soap.
BOTH: Ow. Ow.
The burning is love.
"Russia,
Great Britain and France
had formed
an entente cordiale..."
(groaning)
Ooh, algebra.
I'll just do a few equations.
No. No more distractions.
Hey, Bart, want to go for a ride
in my uncle's
Black Hawk helicopter?
But I just started my paper.
It's your last chance.
He's probably going to get
court-martialed for this.
Black Hawk up.
(both laughing)
(kissing)
BART (over loudspeaker):
Attention, teenage boys.
Take your hands off my daughter.
MILHOUSE: Now kiss each other.
(whimpering)
(laughing)
(whistling)
Grandpa, quick,
tell me everything you know
about World War I.
World War I? I fought in that.
'Course, to enlist,
I had to lie about my age.
(young Grampa):
Want to see my picture I drew?
Lieutenant Simpson,
you've been up for hours.
Take a nap.
You're no good to us cranky.
But I'm not tired.
(crying)
Oh, this is great stuff.
I can pad it out to ten pages.
Goodnight, Grandpa.
But I'm not tired.
Goodnight, sleepyhead.
Do you have to poop?
Always.
"F"? There must be some mistake.
It's as long as you asked for.
Counting six pages of ads.
You're going to have to redo
your paper after class.
Well, if I may dust off
an old chestnut...
Ay, caramba!
Ay, caramba indeed.
And so on November 11th, 1918,
the guns fell silent
and peace returned.
The End.
Very good, Bart.
Oh, I must have
the wrong classroom.
I was looking for my girlfriend,
not Pam Dawber.
(both chuckling)
Are you ready for a little
after school special?
Eyes front, Simpson.
(cell phone ringing)
Hello. Mother?
(groaning)
I'll be right there.
Now she wants
to get out of the tub.
You've got to stop
putting your mother ahead of me.
We have a date.
I'll be back in three hours.
Maybe less.
But almost certainly more.
-(grunts)
-(door closes)
(crying)
He's a wiener, Mrs. K.
Just say the word, and his desk
is full of boogers.
(crying)
That's sweet of you,
but if I lost Seymour,
who else is there?
♪ I believe in miracles ♪
♪ Where you from,
you sexy thing? ♪
♪ Sexy thing, you... ♪
OK, there's a lot of low cards
in that hand.
But, since we're both free,
why don't you and me
hit the town?
A pity date from a ten-year-old?
(sighs) I'll take it.
RAINIER: From the widest gully
to the deepest trench,
holes define who we are
and where we're going.
And, although Rover here
may not know it,
he is participating in a ritual
as old as time itself.
He is giving birth to a hole.
Or, consider the dolphin,
nature's most filmed creature.
Even they have holes--
blowholes.
Thanks for going out
with me tonight.
It really took my mind off
stupid jerks.
And their mothers.
(sighs)
BART: And did you know
the hole's only natural
enemy is the pile?
I can't believe you went
to the movies with a teacher.
What happened
to the Bart Simpson
who put the mothballs
in the beef stew?
Hey, I only hung out
with Krabappel
because Skinner blew her off.
I've never seen her so sad.
You know what made me feel
better about myself?
That award I got
for World's Greatest Dad.
(slurping)
Dad, you bought that
because it was
full of gummy worms.
And you only wanted those
as bait to catch gummy fish.
Which I did.
(chair moves)
Mm! Trophy.
Hey, Bart, you could
nominate Mrs. Krabappel
for an actual award,
The Teacher of the Year.
Then she'll feel appreciated.
They have an award for teaching?
Hey, they have Latin Grammys.
It is so hard to choose nominees
from all these
qualified candidates.
This is the most difficult
one-day-a-year job in the world.
Put in the next tape.
I use humor
to reach my students.
(groaning)
Dead Poets Society has destroyed
a generation of educators.
(laughing)
And so President Kennedy
says to Khrushchev,
"Well, enough jawin'.
Reach for it, pilgrim."
And the missiles are, like,
"Oh, praise Jesus!
Can I hear an 'Amen'?"
♪ Hey, Macarena. ♪
Next!
I'd like to nominate
my teacher, Mrs. Krabappel.
She may not be
glamorous or entertaining.
She's just a real teacher
who comes in every day
no matter what.
And she never gave up on me,
Bart Simpson.
(gasping) The Bart Simpson?
I thought he was just
an urban legend.
If she's danced with the devil
in the blue shorts and lived,
we have ourselves a nominee.
(all) Mm-hmm.
Oh, Lord it's only Wednesday.
I hope one of those little hoods
puts a tack on my chair
just so I can feel something.
(horn blowing and cheering)
What's going on?
Edna Krabappel,
you've been nominated
for Teacher of the Year.
(cheering)
Oh, my God.
(crying)
NELSON: Ha-ha!
You're crying.
Nelson Muntz,
you've been nominated
for Bully of the Year.
Thank you so much.
(crying)
Wedgie!
(grunting)
How does it feel to be nominated
for "Teacher of The Year"?
(laughs) I can't believe it.
This after I accidentally showed
the R-rated Romeo and Juliet.
I thought that nipple
would haunt me forever.
Oh, Reporter Cletus,
Outhouse Times-Picayune.
Is there any persons,
critters or spells
to which you attribute
this accolade?
There's one person
I'd like to thank for this.
Hmm. Hmm.
We've had our ups and downs,
but I can't imagine
life without him--
Bart Simpson.
(crowd cheering)
MAN: Way to go, Bart!
I can't express
how I feel in words
so I drew this picture.
These stink lines stand
for dedication, caring,
and for letting me
drink coffee in class.
Way to go, Edna.
(all cheering)
-Yes, yes!
-Way to go!
Oh, oh. Follow-up query.
Mrs. K, if you win
this here learning derby,
will you forget
your kith and kin
and leave us all forever?
Leave us forever?
I'd better pee on this fire.
(microphone feeds back)
As principal, I'd just like
to say a few words
about what this wonderful woman
means to this school
and to me.
Webster's Dictionary
defines Mrs. Krabappel as...
(pager plays Beethoven's
Fifth Symphony)
Excuse me. I have
an emergency page from Mother.
This press conference is over.
(groans)
So, because I nominated Mrs. K,
our whole family
gets a free trip
to the awards ceremony
in Orlando.
Orlando?
Are we going to Sea World?
-No.
-Disney World?
-Uh-uh.
-Universal Studios?
-'Fraid not.
-Leisure World?
Sorry, Grampa.
-Gator Gulch?
-You wish.
Leisure World?
Grampa, you're not even going.
Wait a minute.
I know where we're going.
Oh, it's horrible!
Oh, it's even boring
to fly over it.
(sobbing)
Oh, God!
It's so exciting.
I'm meeting my peers.
Ooh, the FutureSphere.
It's what
people in 1965 imagined
what life would be like in 1987.
MAN on PA:
Eastern Airlines presents
"The World of Tomorrow."
Don't walk-- fly!--
in your personal
Eastern Airlines Air Buggy.
And say goodbye
to the cola wars.
The victor,
Eastern Airlines Cola.
And we're not stopping there.
Because at Eastern Airlines,
world conquest is part
of our master plan.
Now enjoy the soothing music
of The Turtles.
("Happy Together" playing)
♪ Ba, ba, ba-ba-ba, ba-ba-ba,
ba-ba-ba, ba-ba-ba-ba... ♪
It's nice and cool in here,
don't you think?
MAN ON PA: Welcome to
the electric car of the future
sponsored by the
Gasoline Producers of America.
(car sputtering)
(sad, whiny voice):
Hello, I'm an electric car.
I can't go very fast
or very far.
And, if you drive me,
people will think you're gay.
(chanting) One of us. One of us.
Willie, you're no stranger
to the inner workings
of the female mind.
Aye. Willie's sent many
a Vermont Teddy Bear.
Well, I'm a little worried
that, with all this attention,
Edna may meet someone better.
Damn straight she will,
you branch-eating popinjay!
Your woman's in Orlando, man!
You can't take two steps
there without falling
into a tunnel of love.
Oh, I've been a fool.
I've got to go after her!
Take me car.
(grunts)
(device beeps)
Make sure you fill it up
with Techron gas.
You don't want a case
of the knocks.
Wow, this restaurant
is so international.
"La Pizza, Der Hamburger,
Senor Grilled Cheese."
I hope I don't accidentally
order an elephant.
(laughs)
What happened to you two?
AUDIENCE: Ew!
Let's go make some fireworks
of our own.
I get to tamp the powder.
I wouldn't have it
any other way.
(chuckles)
Oh, I wish I had
someone to share this with.
Edna Krabappel, please report
to the principal's arms.
-Oh, you came!
-(Seymour chuckles)
I took a personal day.
(moaning)
MRS. SKINNER: Seymour!
Bring me some ice!
My fanny is baboon-red
after that car ride.
Ow! Mother, we were sharing
an open-mouthed kiss.
You brought your mother?
(nervous laughter)
Well, technically,
since she's paying for the room,
she brought me.
I am tired of sharing you
with your mother.
This woman carried me
for nine and a half months.
I was out for two weeks,
then went back in.
Hey, Skinner, do you and Edna
want to join Marge and me
at "Great Moments
With Mr. Eisner"?
I believe the only venue for me
is the ride of broken dreams.
Oh, you mean the Enron ride.
Let's go.
WOMAN:
We're all going to be rich!
(all screaming)
MAN: We broke even.
(all groan)
MAN: Mm! That's good satire.
(gasps) Mom...
is that Principal Skinner
sleeping in the bed of tomorrow?
(mechanical voice):
Rise and shine, sleepyhead.
You'll be late for the next
rocket to the moon.
He's never going to get up.
He's got no legs.
What are you doing here?
Hmm. Well, since Edna dumped me,
I've been wandering
around this park all night.
It's educational
and offers mild thrills--
just like Edna.
Now, before the show,
you'll need to take urine tests
to prove you're not taking
teaching-enhancing drugs.
(crazed laugh)
You can't test what's not there!
We're also pleased to announce
that our winner will receive
enough money
so they'll never have
to teach again.
(cheering)
Good Lord, I may lose
Edna forever.
I've got to stop her
from winning.
Then she'll be broken,
miserable and mine.
(indistinct noise)
Don't look back.
Just keep driving.
Seymour? Glad you're here.
You can help me play
"Halloween Hit and Run."
-(screams)
-(grunts)
Ooh, this game is going to get
some disapproving clucks.
But, for now, I need
my tongue to talk to you.
I don't want to lose Edna,
so I need you to sabotage
her chances of winning tonight.
But I don't want to hurt Mrs. K.
All right, Bart, I didn't want
to resort to this, but...
this drawing was found
on the wall
of Springfield Elementary
late last week.
All right, I'm in.
I'll humiliate
the love of your life.
Because I like you
I'll even do it pro boner.
That's pro bono.
I know what I said.
Hmm. This is the worst thing
I've ever done.
Even worse than
what I did in 'Nam.
(mid-'60s rock playing)
You're going to get
your parade...
down my esophagus.
(deep sigh)
So many categories.
Gym Teacher of the Year,
Substitute Teacher of the Year,
Most Wheelchair-Accessible
School award?
Oh, who will take home
the Rampy?
ANNOUNCER: And now,
to present our final award
for Teacher of the Year,
Little Richard.
I love teachers.
In fact, I'm a teacher.
I taught Paul McCartney
to go (sing-song voice) Whoo!
"Purple Rain."
Shut up!
Michael Jackson
just told me to shut up.
We're down to our
last three teachers, folks,
and the winner will be
decided by one final question
asked by the students
who nominated them.
(applause)
SKINNER: I feel terrible
but this is the only way
I can win Edna
without upsetting Mother.
MRS. SKINNER: He has
the tiny hands of a chimp.
And now Bart Simpson
will ask a question
to his teacher.
"W... wha... at...
"Wa...
Wo..."
Hurry up, son.
I'm sorry. I can't read.
Mrs. Krabappel never
taught me to read.
(all gasping)
Is this true, Edna?
(dejected sigh)
Oh, God, I've created
a Prankenstein.
Wait. That boy is lying.
He's not illiterate.
And he's good around
the potty, too.
I'm sorry, everyone.
I perpetrated this charade.
(groans)
The boy can read,
and Edna Krabappel
is the greatest teacher
-I have ever known.
-(gasps)
If she can teach me to love,
then she can teach anything.
ALL: Ah!
MRS. SKINNER: Seymour!
Your feelings are
ugly and wrong.
Are you going to listen to her?
Not on your life, Reverend.
From now on, I'm my own man.
I have waited to hear
that for so long.
And it gets better.
Edna Krabappel...
will you marry me?
-(gasps)
-Now, I must warn you,
two months salary
only bought me the ring box.
Oh, here, honey,
take one of mine.
(sing-song voice) Whoo!
Oh, I felt naked there
for a minute.
(gasps)
Seymour, of course
I'll marry you.
Oh, great.
Three in a bed.
Since the show is running long,
we'll just go ahead
and name a winner.
(chanting): Edna...
Edna...
Julio Estudiante--
an inner-city math teacher
who taught teenage gang members
that differential equations
are more powerful than bullets.
What a rip!
You all should be ashamed!
Well, I didn't win
Teacher of the Year,
but I didn't go home
empty-handed.
Do you want to check out
the bed of tomorrow... today?
Oh, Seymour.
(chuckling)
I love happy endings.
Well, here's ours.
We're going to Disney World!
(grunting)
(sirens wailing)
(voice over bullhorn):
Step away from the wall.
Oh, it's so beautiful.
(grunts)
HOMER: One churro, please.
MAN: That'll be $14.
(Homer screaming and crying)
Here.
♪ Ba, ba, ba, ba-ba-ba ♪
♪ Ba-ba-ba, ba-ba-ba-ba... ♪
Boy those pies look good.
Open your gullet,
you human blob.
Well, what do you think?
(lively musical intro)
What do I think of the pie?
♪ Goodness gracious
it's delicious ♪
♪ That's what I think
of the pie ♪
♪ Because... ♪
Should we follow him?
I'm on vacation.
-(murmuring)
-Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services