(theme music playing)
CHORUS: The Simpsons
D'oh! (screams)
ALL: (shouting and grunting)
(sharks growling)
-Hi, Moe. Got any beer?
-Sure. Check in the fridge.
Wait a minute, I'm at work.
You gotta pay for it.
What the...? Where's my money?
MARGE: Dear Homie, had to buy
diapers for Maggie. Love, Marge.
-Wha...?
-MARGE: Simpson.
Oh.
LISA: Dear Dad, took money
for the school book fair.
BART: Homer, I need cash
or they're gonna break my legs.
Sorry, Homer.
So you're gonna let me
walk out of here sober?
I'm afraid so.
-And you can live with that?
-Ya-huh.
Fine. There are plenty other ways for me
to alter my consciousness.
Oh, yeah.
Are you gonna buy those toads
or just lick them?
Lick them. Go away.
Ah.
Thanks for the donation,
Mr. Simpson. Do you feel OK?
Jewish? Oh, no, I'm not Jewish.
(laughing)
Wait till Moe sees
how wasted I got without him.
He's gonna plotz.
You wouldn't serve Homer just 'cause
he didn't have money?
What happened to you, Moe?
You used to be about the booze.
Oh, yeah. I guess I got caught
up in all the glitz and glamor.
(squeaks)
(hums)
-Well, Moe.
-Homer, I'm so sorry. Have a free beer.
Oh.
Uh, I don't care about the
color of your skin, Lenny.
You're my friend. (chuckles)
Man, I've never seen anybody
get loaded so fast.
Homer, can you say the alphabet backwards?
Oh, you'd like that, wouldn't you? You...
-Hey, I'm worried.
-I've had just about enough of you.
-Oh, yeah?
-Uh-huh.
-Oh, rats.
-I'm out of here.
We can't let our friend drive
like this. I'm liable here.
-Uh...?
-Get his keys.
(grunting)
Hey, you want my keys?
Get them now, jerks.
(laughs) So long, jerks.
(laughing)
(mimics engine rumbling)
Running after the car, huh?
Let's see if you can follow this.
(screaming)
Oh, that's it.
(whistles)
HOMER: (humming)
-MAN: Where to, pal?
-HOMER: Moe's Tavern.
Good morning, everybody.
What's for breakfast, cutie?
Homie, it's 5 p.m. We're having dinner.
What? Wait a... That can't be right.
Wait. Was last night the night
we set the clocks ahead eight hours?
No. It was the night
You got loaded at Moe's
and the car had to be towed home.
If I was that drunk, I would remember it.
It's true. I couldn't even wake
you up for work this morning.
I had to tell Mr. Burns
you had violent diarrhea.
Oh, couldn't you come up
with a less embarrassing lie?
But you did have violent diarrhea.
Nobody open the hallway closet
until I say it's OK.
BOTH: (shuddering)
Do you remember how you got home
last night, Dad?
Of course.
It was, uh, some kind of a light rail.
There's no light rail in Springfield.
Oh, won't anyone pretend to believe me?
-I will, Dad.
-That's why you're my favorite.
All right, time for my favorite show.
MAN (on TV) : MTC... Monkey Trauma Center
will not be seen tonight.
Oh.
MAN: ...so we may proudly
present this much cheaper show.
WOMAN (on TV) : Taxicab Conversations.
Hey, I read about this show
in Teen Modern Maturity.
They film passengers with hidden cameras
and catch them at their most uninhibited.
That explains that.
(disco music playing over speakers)
(humming)
-(imitating disco beats)
-Looks like somebody got down tonight.
Disco Stu always gets down, baby.
Because when the beat is hot, the...
(sighs)
-Hey, can you keep a secret?
-What is it, hon?
I hate disco.
It's all I've talked about for so long,
people think I'm a one-note guy.
(sighs)
It's just getting harder, you know.
I had no idea Disco Stu was so complex.
-How you doing?
-Talky thing, ain't you?
Another proud moment for the Simpsons.
I don't remember anybody telling me
I was gonna be on TV.
(slurping)
So, what do you do for a living?
Oh, you know, I'm a guy at a place.
How'd you get such a crappy job?
You a convict or a junkie?
-Little of both. You got a family?
-Oh, yeah.
Wife and two or three kids.
Can't imagine my life without them.
Oh, you big fooler.
Pretending not to remember
so you could surprise us.
(chuckles) Yeah, I'm pretty great.
At the end of a hard day
there's no better feeling than coming home
to the people that you love.
-Oh, Homie.
-That is so sweet.
I had no idea, Dad.
I just assumed with all the
stranglings, you know...
That my family isn't the center
of my universe?
Are you nuts?
Then there's those other days
where you just wish you never got married
or had kids.
(groans)
One minute, you're a carefree teenager,
with dreams of being a rock
star, or a photographer for Playboy...
then, bam, some babe
gets her claws in you...
Huh?
...and, boom, you got a bunch
of kids that always needs love.
BOTH: (gasping)
So whammo, you get stuck
in some boring job
where they don't let you play guitar
or take pictures of naked women.
And all you can do is watch yourself
get bald and fat
and kiss your dreams goodbye.
(snoring)
Oh, I can't believe they took
Monkey Trauma Center off for this.
(snoring)
Lousy family.
So I'm just some babe
who sank her claws into you.
-A hot babe.
-Oh!
Have you always resented us, Dad?
Oh, I don't resent you, sweetheart.
What I was trying to say,
and maybe I didn't use the right words
was that marriage is like a coffin
and each kid is another nail.
-But as coffins go...
-Please don't say anymore.
Sorry we ruined your life, Homer.
Hmph!
Oh, what have I done?
(alarm whistles)
-Get in.
-What?
Get in.
Hey, what's this suitcase for?
-Are we going on a trip?
-You are.
(laughing)
(whimpers)
Where are you taking me?
A place where you'll never be
bothered by your family again.
(gasps)
Oh.
(whimpers)
(screams)
(tires screech)
Get out of the car, Homer.
You can't just leave me out here.
There's not another woman for miles.
Sorry, Dad.
Maybe now you'll appreciate us.
While you're spending the week at...
Rock 'n' Roll Fantasy Camp.
HOMER: (gasps)
The Rolling Stones' Rock 'n'
Roll Fantasy Camp.
But I thought you guys were mad at me.
For once in my life, I'm confused.
We had a family meeting and decided
that even though what you said about us
was incredibly thoughtless,
and hurtful, you had a point.
-Damn straight.
-You work a job you don't like
so I'm able to be home with the kids.
And you take me places you hate
like museums, plays and the Olive Garden.
And even though you knew
I ratted you out to the IRS,
-you never busted me on it.
-You what?
So to say thank you
for all your sacrifices,
we spent our family vacation
fund on something that's just for you.
-Do you like it?
-You guys are the best.
I love you. I love you.
I love you... Ugh, oh.
I'm OK. I love you.
I love you. I love you.
(owl hooting)
Hey, what gives?
Where are all the rock stars?
I don't know,
but it's starting to get dark.
(guitar plays)
Huh, what was that?
Oh, it's getting closer.
-Hello, campers.
-How you doing?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
It's Mick Jagger and Keith Richards.
(groans)
Welcome to Rock 'n' Roll Fantasy Camp
where you'll experience the complete
rock 'n' roll lifestyle...
without the lawsuits and STDs.
-Whoa! STDs!
-Now, you're all here for one reason...
-To rock!
-Who said that?
That's right, Otto. We're here to rock!
ALL: (cheering)
So get a good night's sleep
and remember, rule number one,
there are no rules.
-ALL: (cheering)
-Rule number two, no outside food.
Oh, what a gyp.
Hey, Mick, you gonna teach us
your cocksure strut?
Not today, I've got a ton of paperwork
to catch up on.
Ah, tell me about it. At my
job, we... Oh, oh, you're gone.
RICHARDS (on PA) : Hey! Wake up!
ALL: (groaning)
Are you ready to receive
professional training in rock?
-Have you been awake all night?
-I am so excited, I couldn't fall asleep.
I even took some pills
I found on the floor and still nothing.
You took pills you found on the floor?
Uh-huh, now I'm afraid that if
I stop talking, I'll die. Isn't Mick cool?
I thought he'd be all like,
"I'm a rock star. Aren't I great?"
But he's just like you or me
or Jesus over there.
-Can I have a guitar?
(whistles) People. People.
If everyone's gonna pick guitar,
I'm not gonna have enough to go around.
Oh, come on.
But there's lots
of other fun instruments...
like bass.
Come on, who'd like to be a bass player?
Out of my way, nerdlinger.
-My image.
-OTTO: Get me the Strat.
Hand me the Strat.
I'm telling Mr. Jagger.
Ooh, "I'm telling Mr. Jagger."
(Lenny Kravitz's "Are You
Gonna Go My Way?" playing)
The clothes you wear on stage should
be a defiant statement of individuality.
HOMER: Like this, Mr. Kravitz?
God, no.
May we talk about, uh, accentuating
the masculine area?
Did you hear that, people? Apu asked
about crotch stuffing.
Now, I don't do it. Kenny Loggins does.
I trusted you!
(sobbing)
Now, a guitar has many, many nicknames.
An ax, a gitbox...
Well, I guess that's it.
Anyway, we're gonna start
with the fundamentals.
Playing a burning guitar with your teeth.
-All right, fire.
-(others cheer)
-Mr. Seltzer?
-Setzer.
No, I think it's Seltzer.
(grunts)
-What is it, Homer?
-I came up with a stage move
I feel is very cool.
(grunting)
(singing) ♪ Baby, baby, baby, baby ♪
We've gotta start using a cheaper oatmeal.
HOMER: Sorry, Mick!
Simpson!
("She's So Cold" playing over speakers)
OK, strut, strut, strut...
...strut, strut, spin, and rooster.
Look, everyone, Homer's got it.
♪ I'm so hot for me I'm so hot for me ♪
♪ I'm so cold ♪
OK, now schoolmarm.
♪ I'm the burning fire ♪
♪ I'm the bleeding volcano ♪
Everybody's naughty
and freeze finish.
WIGGUM: Ow.
And no matter where you are,
always say it's the wildest
town in the whole damn world.
So when you said it in Springfield
last year, you didn't mean it?
Yeah, sure I did.
But only because Springfield really
is the wildest town
in the whole damn world.
-Yes, I knew it. I knew it.
-Springfield!
(guitar playing)
Lyrics are the hardest part
of songwriting.
When you come up with something
meaningful and heartfelt...
-Boring.
-Will you stop saying that?
But rock stars are supposed
to be about drinking
and getting drunk and boozing it up.
And girls that have legs
and know how to use them.
A-- and why I can't drive 55.
You just want mindless generic rock?
Precisely.
(groans)
(strumming a bold tune)
♪ See that drunk girl
speeding down the street? ♪
ALL: Yeah!
♪ She's worried about the state
of public schools ♪
ALL: (booing)
♪ She likes to party, she likes to rock ♪
ALL: Yeah!
♪ She prays that our schools
don't run out of chalk ♪
ALL: (booing)
(guitar fades)
Getting away from the gig can be a matter
of life and death.
So you gotta be in great physical shape.
OK, follow me.
(audience cheering over speakers)
-Paparazzi to the left.
-I got them.
(grunting)
I'm entitled to a private life.
I'm not a role model and so forth.
Good, Homer. Now, just past
the groupies and we're home.
WOMAN (on recording) : I love you.
Please sleep with us.
They're bloody cardboard.
We know.
(guitars playing)
♪ You ain't never caught a rabbit ♪
♪ And you ain't no friend of mine ♪
-Yeah!
-ALL: (screaming)
Well, what do you think?
Uh, you rock, Homer.
Really? You really think
I'm better than you?
That was great, Homie.
-What the hell are you doing here?
-Camp is over, Homer.
-It's been a week already?
-I'm glad you had fun.
-But it's time to come home.
-Your mother's right, Homer.
Gotta get back to the real world.
Yeah, we've all gotta get home.
My lawn's not gonna mow itself.
And I've gotta put up the storm windows.
Winter's coming.
HOMER: Wait. Don't go.
I wanna keep on rocking.
Come on, guys. A-one, a-two...
I'll take that.
No!
(sobbing)
It came with a pick.
(groans softly)
Come on, Dad.
No! No! I won't go. You can't make me!
-Dad, you knew this day was coming.
-I knew nothing.
Ugh, stop kicking me, Dad.
Never.
(sobs)
My dream has been shattered
into shards of a broken dream.
I was so close to being a rock star,
but now, there's a chance
it might not happen.
I'll just have to settle for being a fat,
bald, fat nothing.
Finally. Can we go now?
Now, before I lock the door,
do you have to go to the bathroom?
No, I'm fine.
Ugh, I'm so despondent.
Cheer up, Homer.
It's only rock 'n' roll camp.
But I like it.
(sobbing)
Tell you what, we're doing a benefit gig
before we leave town.
How would you like to join us on-stage?
-For serious?
-For serious, Homer.
Can I have 40 guest passes?
Woo-hoo!
Wow, all access.
All access.
Ooh, good thing it's laminated. (laughs)
(grunts)
-Sir, you can't...
-All access.
Oh, sorry.
(humming)
WOMEN: (screaming)
-HOMER: All access.
-WOMAN 1: Ooh.
- Nice.
-WOMAN 2: You rock.
(indistinct chatter)
Wow, Homer. I ain't had front row seats
since my Moonie wedding.
After the show, you can come
backstage for pizza and pop.
-Yes!
-All right!
Now, that's a winning combination.
Here you go. Front and center.
I'm so proud of you, Homie.
It's like you're Kid Rock
and I'm Pamela Anderson Lee Rock.
CROWD: (cheering)
Ooh, gotta run. Enjoy the show.
(mask surface squeaking)
OK, let's see the eyes.
Now the fire.
Thanks, mate.
Couldn't you find
a more fuel-efficient Satan?
Lenny, don't you have a crotch to stuff?
Evening, fellow rockers.
There you are. We thought
we were going to go on without you.
I'm ready. Just give me a guitar.
How many solos should I do?
Four? I'll do four.
Uh, Homer, you didn't think you were
gonna be playing with...
(gasps) My official tour jacket. Lookit...
Wait. You misspelled "guitar hero."
Look, sorry if there's been
a misunderstanding, Homer.
We really just need you
to tap the mikes and say,
-"Test, test."
-Can't you do it?
Oh.
OK. So I'll, uh...
OK.
AUDIENCE: (cheering)
-Look, there's Dad!
-Woo-hoo! Yay, Homer!
I'm his groupie. (giggles)
Am I saying that right? Groupie?
-Yeah!
-WOMAN: Yeah, Homer!
CARL: You're the man, Homer!
You're the man!
LENNY: You rock the house!
Let's go, Homer!
MOE: It's go time! It's go time!
Test. Test.
Why is he performing
the duties of a roadie?
Am I saying that right? Roadie?
Test, test. Check, check.
-Hey, he's not rocking out at all.
-Test.
Test. Test.
♪ You're testing my love for you ♪
♪ Check, check ♪
♪ You're checking to see if I'm true ♪
CROWD: (cheering)
♪ Test one, test two
test three, test four ♪
♪ You test me like the water
in El Salvador ♪
-Whoa, El Salvador!
-What's all this then?
He's stealing the show from us.
JAGGER: Not on my shift.
Let's rock 'n' roll.
ALL: (cheering)
♪ Baby, baby, baby, baby, baby ♪
Uh-oh.
(screams)
No!
CROWD: (cheering)
Oh, yeah. It's good to see
the spectacle back in rock.
ALL: (screaming)
Did you know it was gonna
turn into a riot, Dad?
Oh, yeah.
When you've been in as many as I have,
you can sense them coming.
-Did they ever find Tom Petty's toe?
-What am I, the lost and found?
There's no excuse
for our horrible behavior tonight, Homer.
We acted like a bunch of angry young men.
Rock 'n' roll is supposed
to be about peace and love.
I hope you won't judge the entire
Brian Setzer Orchestra by my actions.
What we're trying to say,
Homer, is we're sorry.
By the way, I don't suppose
any of you have seen my, um...
-No. Sorry.
-Oh.
There's no need for apologies,
guys. You're rock stars.
You're supposed to be reckless
and destructive
and be celebrated for behavior
that would land normal people in jail.
That's what I told them, Homer.
Just the same,
we'd like to make it up to you.
We're doing a gig tomorrow
to benefit the victims of tonight's gig.
And we'd consider it an honor
if you join us.
Well, you're very sweet, Mick.
But the only rocking I wanna do
is in my living-room chair
surrounded by the world's
greatest backup group,
my family.
(over radio) ♪ There goes the last DJ ♪
Are you sure you don't miss hanging out
with your rock-star friends, Dad?
No, I got something to remember them by.
(laughs)
-Have fun at school, kids.
-Later, Homer.
Mr. Simpson, this zone
is for school buses only.
(screams)
KIDS: (laughing)
Rock 'n' roll! Woo-hoo.
KIDS: (cheering)
("Rip This Joint" playing over speaker)
♪ Papa says no ♪
♪ Make up you mind 'cause I gotta go ♪
♪ I'm gonna raise hell at the Union Hall ♪
♪ Drive myself right over the wall ♪
♪ Rip this joint gonna save your soul ♪
♪ Round and round and round we go ♪
♪ Roll this joint gonna get down low ♪
♪ Start my starter gonna stop the show ♪
And I've gotta put up the storm windows.
Winter's coming.
Everybody's naughty and freeze finish.
♪ She likes to party she likes to rock ♪
HOMER: Yeah!
But there's lots of other fun
instruments, like bass.
I hope you won't judge the entire
Brian Setzer Orchestra by my actions.
Rock 'n' roll is supposed to be
about peace and love.
-Who said that?
-Will you stop saying that?
ALL: (laughing)
JAGGER: Simpson!
Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services