CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(humming)
Three minutes, forty seconds--
a new personal best!
Maggie?
(coughing)
(haughty grunt)
Mmm.
No one will ever know.
HOMER: Mail call!
Oh, anything good?
The George Foreman Mail Sorter
will let us know.
(whirring)
(sizzling)
Mmm!
"Your family is invited
to a free weekend
at Stagnant Springs Spa."
Ooh, that place is famous.
It's where J. Lo hit
P. Diddy upside the head
with Gary Coleman.
Our attendants can take
ten years off your face
and stick it in your boobs.
And this place isn't
just for gals anymore.
It's also for vain, effeminate men.
(squeaking)
Kent Brockman?
Well, if you find this
shocking, look at Tom Brokaw.
(machine whirring)
(clicks)
Truly, that was the greatest regeneration.
This place blows.
I'm going to go float a Baby Ruth
down the mineral bath.
Don't worry, kids.
We've got something just for you.
Do you like Dr. Seuss?
-No.
-Then you'll love Dr. Mas-seuss.
Bad posture has floobled
and snozzled your neck.
I'll stop talking like this
if you write me a check.
(slurping)
Ooh...
These turtles know
just where the knots are.
It just shows you
God has a plan for every creature.
Yes, yes, indeed.
(cracking)
(sloshing)
(gasps): Ooh! Uh... help, please!
Someone throw me a stick!
Don't struggle.
You'll only sink faster.
Roll your eyes back into your head,
focusing on your breathing.
You should feel a pleasant tingling.
Oh, I do! I do!
(Marge grunting)
Now, get down on all fours
with your rear in the air.
What position is this?
The American taxpayer!
Hmm.
(sighing)
(gasping)
(Homer's inner voice)
Oh, my God, a naked celebrity.
Be cool. Don't stare at his famous wang.
Ha, ha, ha! Go ahead, look.
The whole world already saw it
in Nudist Camp Commandant.
I wore nothing!
"Do not use steam room
if you are overweight
or have a heart condition."
D-ohh!
Wait a minute. I'm not wearing a shirt!
(yelling)
(groaning)
(humming)
(grunts)
Who ordered the steamed Gentile?
Mm, steamed Gentile.
CHIEF WIGGUM: Don't worry,
us pigs will catch this killer.
Now, Mr. Simpson, is it possible
you're living a double or triple life
that your wife doesn't know about?
Triple? No. Definitely, no.
You have to do something
to protect my husband.
Where on my badge does it say anything
about protecting people?
Uh, second word, Chief.
Thanks, Princeton Pete.
Now, your case requires
someone who understands
the twisted mind of a murderer
and I know just where to find him.
-Paris?
-No. No, not Paris.
(sighs): I'm never going to go to Paris.
These are our most dangerous criminals.
Each one crazier than the last.
Uh, come to think of it he should be there
and this guy-- he should be over there.
Wait. You saying he's crazier than I am?
That's exactly what I'm saying,
Decapitating Harry.
Now, move it.
(screaming gibberish)
Yeah. Yeah, whatever.
I don't think this was a great place
to bring the children.
It still beats Disney's
California Adventure.
Mm-hmm.
-Oh, yeah, it's true.
-Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
So, which one of these psychos
is going to help me catch my killer?
He's right in here.
(beeps)
COMPUTER VOICE: Access denied.
Oh, fine, I got to use a fork.
(door opens)
Hello, Bart.
(screaming) BOTH: Sideshow Bob!
Oh, come now.
We've been through so much together.
Just call me "Bob."
(screaming)
BOTH: Bob!
All right, Bob, if you help us catch
the guy trying to kill Homer,
we'll make it worth your while.
What could you possibly offer me?
Your pick of roles in the prison musical.
This year I think it's Man of La Mancha.
Yeah, Don Quixote,
Sancho Panza, Dr. Carrasco,
you know, they're all great parts.
Ah, what a great show.
I wish it was today.
So what do you say, Bob?
Fair enough.
(groans)
Now, I will need round-the-clock access
to all the Simpsons.
Especially Bart.
Well, then, you might as well
to stay with us.
We serve the same meat the prisons do.
Wait, wait, wait. Bob can't stay with us.
This man has tried to kill me so much
it's not funny anymore.
Don't worry, son.
We have ways of making him compliant.
Dad, I can't believe
you're putting my life at risk
to save your own.
You'll understand someday
when you have kids.
Now, if he even looks at you funny
this shock garter will set him straight.
And don't try taking it off
because it's taped to your leg hair.
And that really hurts.
Oh, come now.
As gentlemen, surely
we can just agree to...
-(shock garter goes off)
-Ack! Gah!
-Sorry.
-Fair enough.
But now that we know what it can do,
there's no need to... Mother! Aah!
Wow, you don't even
have to point it at him.
(buzzing and yelling)
Homer, think carefully.
Of all the people you have known,
who might have reason to do you ill?
Hmm... well, there's Mr. Burns,
Fat Tony, the Emperor of Japan,
ex-President Bush.
The late Frank Grimes.
PBS, Stephen Hawking,
the fat little Dixie Chick...
And the state of Florida.
How can one ordinary man
have so many enemies?
I'm a people person... who drinks.
Ah.
Homer, in order
to identify your assailant,
I must follow you through the course
of a normal day.
Just do what you usually do
and the killer will reveal himself.
Gotcha.
This is a normal day?
I just wanted to impress you.
Welcome to your Springfield
Mardi Gras headquarters.
Cast your vote now for this year's king.
HOMER: Ooh, Mardi Gras.
Didn't last year's king have to abdicate
because he married a commoner?
And I'd do it again.
But I do miss the Royal Crown Cola.
Ah, yes, the Kwik-E-Mart.
I haven't been here since I robbed it
dressed as Krusty.
My one successful crime.
You were quite the gentlemen.
Today's robbers,
they are all smash-and-grab.
You understood the dance.
Our time is passing, old friend.
Uh, if you two country hens are
finished clucking,
I'd like to buy a copy of Jugs and Ammo.
Well, we've settled that argument.
You can't read a magazine and drive.
Look, junior, I expect this to be fixed
with quality GM parts!
But your car was built in Croatia.
It's made from old Soviet tanks.
Just fix it, Mr. Sasswrench!
Homer, please.
The last thing you need is more enemies.
Right, right.
I'm counting the pennies in the ashtray.
There's two!
(squeaking)
The trap is set.
The killer will think this dummy
is you out for an evening stroll.
Now we lie in wait
like hungry Cassius for noble Caesar.
You're so smart.
Shock him.
(anguished yell)
(machine squeaking)
Ooh, someone's coming.
Huh, ugh, ugh!
Now who's the sociopath, huh?
Moe!
He's got a dark side
I've never dreamed of.
Well, mystery solved.
Wait a moment...
Oh... he's hurt.
-Go, go, go!
-(tires screeching)
These are Homer's friends and family.
They don't want him dead.
They just want him to suffer.
Aiyaa!
(grunting)
Thank you, Lord.
Once I kill you, everyone
will think I'm the real Homer.
(laughing)
None of this seems odd to you?
Nah.
Say, Bob, how come you were
never able to kill Bart?
Yeah, a kid should be real simple to kill.
I'd just come behind him with a knife
and slit his throat real quick-like.
Guys, Bob is my only hope.
Back off and give him some room to think!
Homer, if I could write haikus
while skinheads beat me with soap,
I can concentrate anywhere.
(gasps)
Oh, my God!
He's getting closer!
Ah, my poor jar.
Oh, why didn't I take more photos?
(sighs)
♪ Memories ♪
♪ Like the corners of my mind... ♪
Here's an interesting clue.
Homer's assailant left a black smudge
on the spa invitation.
This could be the breakthrough we...
(chuckles)
I thought I could get it
while it was in the recharger.
(screaming)
I... what's wrong?... Oh...
I don't know how we ever
had fun without him.
(man on TV) We now return
to That '30s Show.
Hey, Pop, where's the crank
on this Victrola?
Why, it's the latest model.
From now on, the only crank
-in this house is your Aunt Gladys!
-(audience laughing)
For your information, I'm cranky
because I've got polio.
Oh!
(laugh track playing)
Tom Shales gave this show a good review
and I'm the one in prison!
Uh, Bob, I know you're enjoying
Fall Preview Week,
but I was wondering
if you made any progress
towards finding Homer's killer?
No, I haven't.
Go ahead, shock me.
Well, just a little one.
(babbling)
Homer, it's stuck!
(grunting)
Whew. (gasping)
Listen, Homer, I don't know
who your killer is,
but I do know he'll strike again.
Your only hope is to stay
completely out of sight.
Very well. I am gone!
(grunts)
Don't look at me.
-(knocking)
-MAN: Homer Simpson?
Right here.
-(horns honking)
-(jazz music plays)
You've been elected King of Mardi Gras!
Whoo-hoo! Good things
do happen to bad people.
Honey, the King of Mardi Gras
has to ride around on a float all day.
You'll be a sitting duck.
Marge, you're embarrassing me
in front of the drag queen.
(chuckles)
It's Mardi Gras time in Springfield!
This year's Mardi Gras King is
none other than
local hothead Homer Simpson.
Long live the king!
In a related story,
Homer Simpson may not have long to live.
Homer, it's a trap.
You only won because
somebody stuffed the ballot box...
with these.
Nonetheless, the people have spoken.
But I'm afraid you'll get hurt.
Marge, this is a way
to flush this killer out
once and for all...
and get drunk on a Tuesday.
Today's Tuesday, and you've had six beers.
But I'm not drunk!
(crowd cheering)
The killer is out there.
I would stake my entire fortune
of cigarettes on it.
Now, Bob, I know you're concerned,
but don't worry.
I have operatives working the crowd.
So, uh, you're from Tempe?
I'm from Chicago.
Whoa! I'm so drunk I'm going to puke.
Ever get that feeling, beautiful?
(crowd cheering)
America loves its Kings,
from George III to Larry.
(gunshots fired)
(gasps)
(man grunts)
Whew! Just Italians.
His float's already moving.
I didn't even hear the engine start.
Yeah, it's really running quiet.
Some mechanic tuned it up right
before the parade.
A mechanic?
(suspenseful music plays)
(no audio)
(rattling)
My God, that's it!
Homer, you must get off that float!
The brake line has been cut!
(float creaking)
Oh, my God!
Attention drunken idiots,
this is your king!
Sacrifice yourselves to slow me down!
(gulps)
(yells and grunts)
Ooh, that's heavy!
(screams)
(grunts)
Hey, how 'bout some beads?
They're not for dudes!
That's cool.
LISA: Dad's heading straight
for the Museum of Swordfish!
That museum has been nothing
but trouble since it opened.
Must... save... buffoon.
(wheels squeaking)
(screams)
Huh?
Ha, ha! I did it!
Wha-Wha... Huh?
You saved my life!
I've saved a life.
And it feels wonderful.
And yet, I could just as easily
drop you to your death.
Don't be so sure.
I've got my legs wrapped
around your ass pretty tight.
(gunshot)
Everything going dark... like Duff Stout
the beer that made Ireland famous!
I love you, Doris!
I... ooh...
Ooh, we're up so high.
Where could that shot have come from?
There's your killer!
Well, duh!
(grunts)
Your king needs these stilts!
Jesus is our only king!
Not anymore.
(grunts)
There he is!
Hey, I know you.
You're my mechanic, Junior.
Frank Grimes Junior!
Frank Grimes?
Don't you remember?
Your ape-like incompetence drove
my father insane.
Frank Grimes...
What's this?
"Extremely High Voltage."
Well, I don't need safety gloves because
I'm Homer Simps--
(electricity crackling)
Oh, yeah!
How is Old Grimey?
He's dead!
Like you should be!
Whoa! Whoa!
Wait, Frank Grimes wasn't married.
How could he have a son?
He happened to like hookers, OK?
Dad, I figured it out!
The murderer is--
We know-- Frank Grimes Junior.
Huh?
Precisely.
Take him away, boys.
That's nice work, Bob.
Now give him the rhino tranqs.
(delirious babbling)
If I can tranq out
just one freak on stilts,
I know I've done my job.
You're living the dream, Chief.
Dad, I'm really glad you're still alive.
Yeah, it's every parent's dream
to outlive their children.
Good night, son.
Hello, Bart.
(screams)
(groans)
Looking for this?
Now I'm going to take some advice
that was given to me by Lenny
and kill you without delay.
One thrust and the deed is done.
I...
I can't do it.
Huh? Why not?
Well, I guess I've...
Dear God... grown accustomed to your face!
I've grown accustomed
♪ To his face ♪
♪ And dreams of gouging out his eyes ♪
♪ I've grown accustomed to my hate ♪
♪ My plans to lacerate ♪
♪ To disembowel ♪
♪ To hear him howl ♪
♪ The very reason that I live ♪
♪ Is plotting how to watch him die... ♪
(knocking)
HOMER: Bart, turn down that original
cast recording and go to sleep!
♪ I know this chubby scalawag ♪
♪ Has made my life a living hell ♪
♪ Surely, if I drank his blood ♪
♪ I'd be at peace, but, well... ♪
♪ You've grown accustomed to my face... ♪
This isn't a duet!
Sorry.
♪ I've grown accustomed to your fear ♪
♪ Accustomed to revenge ♪
♪ Accustomed to your ♪
♪ Face ♪
(panicked grunts)
We shall meet again, old friend.
But now, I must steal away into the night.
(electrical zapping)
(babbling)
(theme music playing)
-(murmuring)
-Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services