Previously on the shield...
I can't run.
Right now it's about keeping you alive.
You've got history with these grenade tossers.
The guy with the grenades is named guardo.
but he got away.
He screwed my ex-wife.
Sole purpose. Making this investigation
seem like a personal vendetta.
He may have assassinated a gang leader.
This was not part of the deal.
Sure it was. The part antwon didn't tell you about.
This was a calculated move by lieutenant kavanaugh
to put curtis' life in jeopardy
to compel him to testify against his team.
My client is willing to plead to new charges
as long as we can reasonably guarantee his safety.
What does he have to say about his friends?
- Nothing.
- There is one other option, though.
I can't turn on my family.
We're gonna lose a vast
chance at nailing, Vic.
You got to make him believe
that Lemansky gave it up
for witness protection.
Lemansky's talking.
Now all this bullshit can blow back on me.
If he had a change of heart, he would've tipped us.
Well, he wouldn't if his deal meant us going down.
We go to the spot and we'll take his temperature.
If he doesn't show, assume he made the deal.
We got to wait until you get to mexico.
It's all set up.
I'm not going that route.
Then why did you even come back here
if you weren't planning on leaving?
I came to see you guys.
I brought you some food.
Shane.
Are you happy, detective mackey?
Break 'em up.
I'm gonna find out who did this.
I wanna kill 'em.
and then it came to me
just what i had done
and all for no reason
just one piece of lead
i hung my head
here in the courthouse
the whole town was there
i see the judge
high up in his chair
explain to the courtroom
what went through your mind
and we'll ask the jury
what verdict they find
i felt the power
of death over life
i orphaned his children
i widowed his wife
i begged their forgiveness
i wish i was dead
i hung my head
i ran down the grocery guy's contacts.
No one's seen guardo.
He's a goddamn ghost.
Anything south of the border?
Our federale is neck-deep
in some prison beef.
Couldn't help.
How did guardo get lem
to show up at that place?
Alone.
And the way he died.
Shit.
We find guardo...
He dies the same way.
Only slower.
Yeah. He will.
If only he'd reach out to us instead of becca.
- He should've trusted us.
- He was scared.
- If i didn't let the whole thing with antwon go shit-side up...
- It's nobody's fault.
You were a great cop.
You were a great friend.
Here's the 21 you deserve, man.
partner go home?
Billings takes 9 to 5 very seriously.
Another homicide volunteer?
to lemansky's murder.
First two didn't get one detail right.
This guy wasn't even in the country
when it happened.
Guy turns himself in,
keeps the heat off the gang.
He? What he?
out of downtown.
No police funeral. No press conference.
It's like lemansky never wore a badge.
He's ready to be processed.
Vic check in yet?
No. I'll get this.
Hey, is vic around? I can't get him on the phone.
No. He's still taking some personal time.
He's not supposed to be back until tomorrow.
Is everything ok?
I haven't heard from him in days.
I leave messages. He doesn't get back to me.
The kids are freaking out.
Well, i'm sure he's just sorting things out.
Yeah.
I'll get a message to him.
Have him call me.
A.c., sorry to startle you.
Can i get a minute of your time?
What now, lieutenant?
I just wanna apologize for my behavior last week
in captain wyms' office.
- It was out of line. I let it get too personal.
- Yeah, you did.
I've been doing a lot of soul searching
in the light of lemansky's death,
- trying to locate my motives.
- Motives for what?
For finding his killer.
That's not your job.
Wyms' office is in charge of that investigation.
I know.
And wagenbach, he's a good man.
But he's only looking at this from the salvadoran angle.
What do you want, jon?
Same thing i wanted last week.
Not gonna happen. You can't see the line anymore.
Nobody can see the line. Mackey just keeps moving it.
Please. I just need...you need a time for a dead cop.
He deserves that.
Ok. What is it?
The brick of tar that we found on lemansky
was a part of something dirty that vic put into motion.
When curtis got caught,
vic need to protect himself.
So he let lemansky take the plea
while he brokered a deal with antwon mitchell
for his guy's safety in the joint.
But the mitchell deal went bad.
Curtis, he panicked, on the run.
Vic knew that this guy was gonna crack,
- that curtis was gonna
- mackey killed his own guy?
More than likely, he cut a deal with the salvadorans.
But somebody put that grenade in lemansky's lap.
And vic, he knows who did it.
Let wagenbach follow the salvadoran trail.
Let me look into vic.
Discreet. Respectful.
I want your report end of day tomorrow.
We'll decide if it makes sense to pursue.
You'll have it.
Thank you, sir.
There's nothing new on lem.
We've been spending more time knocking down false confessions.
It's all a smokescreen. It's guardo.
We stepped on his drug protection play twice.
Killing lem was a message to stay away.
Been waiting on you. Water street methadone
clinic got torched.
- Go check that out.
- We're not arson patrol.
Well, it's a drug rehab in a heavy gang area.
I can't sign off on you working lem's murder.
Take a step back. Focus on something else.
If we find something out, we'll let you know.
Hey, um, corrine was here last night.
She hadn't heard from you. The kids were worried.
Maybe you should call her.
Right.
Shit. Split. Split.
Hey!
- Hey!
- Turn that shit off.
Come here. Come here.
How's antwon's favorite errand bitch?
- You got a need?
- Yeah. To do this.
- Damn, i got leftovers older than you.
- Yeah, but not as tasty.
Hey, looks like moses finally made it
to the land of milk and underage honey.
- She legal and all kind of willin'.
- Vic.
Goddamn. Looks like business has been good.
No thanks to you. Goddamn empty safe.
Look like your daddy might have to
break on sugar, darlin'.
You wanna get off the dead-banger's list,
you learn to play by the rules.
The first one is, we still make the rules.
Burnt-out clinic on water. That's a 1-9er block.
Looks like you guys might be holding the match.
- We got no beef with the methadonians.
- No?
- They good business.
- How's them climbing off the horse help you?
What we lose in h we gain in benzos.
Some of them junkies drop 10 tabs a day.
- Clinic knows that's going on?
- They don't give a shit.
Getting clean's big money.
Turns those street junkies into state-sponsored ones.
Hell, yeah.
Some of them zombies been on the m-dose 20 goddamn years.
Shit.
Get a hold of the torched clinic.
See if anybody violent's trying to kick their dose.
- Someone on the jones?
- Hurting. Delusional.
I'd be setting fires.
Call wyms. Have her post units at all the methadone facilities.
You, tell your fearless leader, you ever need a favour, shouldn't hesitate to call.
I owe him one.
Clinic said
********methadone kick.
This idiot's lowering his own dosage?
Down to 30 mils.
****by big medicine.
Threatened a counselor. Lives here with his best friend.
No one's seen either of them for 2 days.
Kitchen's clear.
Bedroom's clear.
Looks like quentin's seen some time in the desert.
Probably where he picked up his habit.
- You smell that?
- Yeah.
Ah.
Smells like burnt toast.
Kevin Smith. The roommate.
Cracked his skull open, went through
his wallet, left him for dead.
I'm glad this guy's his best friend.
I'd hate to see what he'd do to his enemies.
Thank you.
- Got anything new on the lemansky murder?
- N... No.
Uh, i called you actually.
Is there any way to get in touch with your el salvadoran c.i.?
Emolia? What do you wanna talk to her for?
Guardo's my lead suspect. She's seen him,
knows that world.
Figured out maybe she's got a pipeline.
She talked about going to seattle, be with her sister.
I really don't know where she is right now.
Um, you parking here?
- I thought your investigation was over.
- It is. I'm opening a new one
in conjunction with lemansky's death.
I'm creating a timeline for my lead suspect.
Who is that?
This is footage from the city and freeway cams
on the night that lemansky was murdered.
In his voluntary statement given the next morning,
mackey said,
"it was too late to see my kids,
"so i hopped on the 10,
"headed towards the coast highway.
That drive always clears my head."
you're establishing a timeline for vic
on the night of the murder?
Yeah.
Uh...um...
Lemansky and mackey were extraordinarily tight.
Plus you've got no motive.
Here's the thing, man.
I had aceveda tell mackey
that lem was cutting a deal,
that he was giving up vic and his team for immunity.
I knew that mackey would go to curtis
to try to find out the truth.
So we were gonna tail him, get him on aiding and abetting.
But vic and his guys, they shook up.
A couple of hours later,
I see him standing by lemansky's body.
Jesus christ.
Maybe it wasn't mackey. Maybe he couldn't do it.
But he needed it done.
He had lem killed because i gave him up.
All right, let's get an a.p.b. out on quentin.
Ex-military. Probably has guns.
Let's track down family members,
drug dealers.
And let's ask our clinic guy...
what's up?
What?
Have you seen this?
Claudette, you knew about this shit?
- I read it.
- Lem gave 12 years to this department,
god knows how many arrests.
****** for any of that.
********************
*******couldn't control the spin.
That's bullshit. Charles is been looking
for corruption goat since he made chief.
- He pinned the horns on lem.
- It's a shitty ending to an ugly story.
And with the bad cop buried,
you and the department get a fresh start, right?
What happened to Lemansky
is an awful thing, I'm sorry.
but he made the choice to stash
the heroin in his car.
- He made the choice to run.
- Kavanaugh browbeat that admission on him.
then he threatened him
to dump him in Antwon's bottom bunk.
- He ran 'cause he was scared.
- He forced lem to make another deal.
What are you talking about?
Becca said that lem made a second deal
with kavanaugh and the chief.
The only way lemansky would make another deal
was if he turned in other dirty cops, and he didn't.
- What?
- It was the same deal.
He was willing to do more time if I.A.D. could assure him
they keep him out of antwon's reach.
- He was killed before it went through.
- No.
Police council is making a formal statement this evening.
We'll be as respectful as we can.
Let me guess.
- That respectful face is aceveda's.
- What do you think?
aceveda said that lem gave us up,
that he told him about the money train.
Kavanaugh must've heard a rumor,
*************************
******** put us in motion.
And we goddamn ate it up.
Made me think my own guy turned on me.
Hey, julien, what the hell is kavanaugh doing here?
Heard he's working lemansky's murder with dutch.
According to his visa stamp,
**********************************
******** lemansky was killed.
He says he's got 2 cousins who saw him kill lemansky.
Um, cousins got addresses?
He doesn't know.
- Right.
- I need a minute with you.
Ok.
Um, run the cousins' names through i.n.s., dmv.
See if you can find addresses.
Kavanaugh's working lem's murder?
- An angle of it, and it's not my choice.
- Which angle?
He didn't really go into any detail.
Don't dick me around, dutchman.
You're the angle.
Hey.
Oh, hey. Oh, i'm sorry.
That's ok. I was just taking a minute.
Oh, my god.
Wow. He's big.
He's beefy and happy.
You mind if, uh...
- No. Here.
- Hey. It's ok.
I just had to take care of some insurance stuff,
- so i thought i'd show him off.
- Yeah.
- He's beautiful, danielle.
- Thanks.
- See you.
- Yeah.
Say bye.
Let's go inside. Come on.
**************************
****Right, lieutenant?
Why would you wanna do that?
************************
******ends up dead.
I'm not at liberty
to discuss the details of my investigation with you.
You get my best friend blown up.
You come into my house.
You hang your mistake and your guilt on me.
Detail enough?
I know this must be the grief talking.
At what point do your bosses realize
you're as delusional as that sick,
crazy,
twisted ex-wife of yours?
I guess the same time that yours realize
that you've murdered two
of your own team members.
Mackey! Kavanaugh!
Knock it off! Knock it off!
- Get your hands off.
- Now!
Jesus. I got a goddamn lump.
What the hell was that?
It's not the first time.
He and mackey went at it at lemansky's crime scene.
- Took 9 unis to break it up.
- Shhhh. This is you being discreet?
Mackey advanced on me both times.
It was self-defense. You saw that.
*****************************
******of the department.
******** pissing matches.
I don't need that report.
- You're done with mackey. You're off of this.
- C'mon...
Get your ass out of the barn
before i hit you with an insubordination beef.
Ok, look, stop.
I have proof that vic had lemansky killed.
I do.
What proof?
Emolia Melendez.
Vic used her to get a message to the el salvadorans.
She set up Lem's murder for Vic.
You told Dutch that you didn't know where she was.
I don't. She called me. She was terrified.
*********************************
************revenue source.
Is there anything this woman won't say for a buck?
Mackey threatened her kid.
- She was terrified. She had no choice, all right?
- You're just bringing this to us now?
************************************
*********had around his neck.
I don't even know who to trust around here anymore.
I me*n, you gave me to the end of the day,
and i was just trying to put the pieces together
before i brought them to you.
Let's bring her in. Let's hear her.
- All right.
- D.e.a. Gave us some leads to where emolia might be.
Dutch is out there writing them down.
Great. I'll give him a call.
Emolia, it's jon. Jon kavanaugh.
- What the hell are you doing here?
- You alone?
Sebastio's at my mom's. Why?
The detective said he wasn't coming here, right?
No. What's the matter?
No toys.
- What, Sebastio's spending all this time at your mom's?
- Yeah. He's safe there.
What are you afraid of?
I snitched on guardo.
People know. They want me dead.
What about Vic?
- He hasn't got your back now?
- Vic ain't shit for me.
Not taking care of you anymore?
Him and his guys shit all over me.
Called sebastio a retard.
That's wrong. I'm sorry about that.
But i have a way to make things right.
Jesus.
Lem didn't rat.
You made me believe my own guy turned on me.
I have people waiting in my office.
You were in bed with kavanaugh the whole time.
Y'know, Kavanaugh played us both.
Squeezed me, too.
- I had no choice.
- Bullshit.
Your jones to hurt me ********
*********he was doing to lem.
You knew about the antwon threat.
That scare put him on the run,
got him killed.
What, so it's my fault? Huh?
When do you ever take responsibility, Vic?
When is anything your fault?
- If you weren't a heartbeat away from being forced out right now--
- what?
What? You'd take my badge?
Go ahead.
Is that what you and Kavanaugh want?
Take it all. Here.
Take it!
What the hell are you doing?
You wanna end a career?
you do it straight up,
to someone who's still alive,
who could still look you right in the eye!
I'm sorry about Lem.
Then don't disgrace him!
You know, it's not my fault.
It's not my call.
I'm just the face of the decision.
I say that vic used me as a middleman
to set up the hit on his guy.
Yes. He had it all planned out.
Give the exact time and place where lem will be.
We'll go over the exact details later.
this kind of thing.
Vic did this.
I''m just trying to get you to tell the truth.
It's just somebody else's truth, that's all.
I won't get in trouble?
You're gonna tell 'em that he threatened your son,
that, uh... That you were scared
and you had no other choice but to do this.
And i'll get all those things?
A house with a pool.
Monthly checks.
This is real, emolia.
It might be my mom.
Emolia melendez? You in there?
It's detective wagenbach.
I just need to ask you a few questions.
You're not in trouble.
Ma'am? Excuse me.
Ma'am.
I need a place where vic would wanna meet you.
It needs to be a public place where it's not very crowded.
Uh, sewing shop. Um...
Did some work for them the other day.
Do you speak english?
Um, excuse-- gracias.
Hello. Wagenbach.
Dutch, jon kavanaugh.
Did the captain call you?
No. Why?
Emolia reached out to me.
I'm on my way to meet her.
She's at tama's costura, a sewing shop on haden.
Are you sure about that?
I got some possible 20s from calls her sister made.
I think she's dodging my knock at one of 'em.
You do whatever you want,
but i would think a sewing shop
would be a great place
to follow up your guardo lead.
But this is your case.
Ok, i'll meet you there.
And then what did he do?
Shot out the door,
called me a sick shithead, and then tried to cap me.
Got this diving out of the way.
Do you have any idea who it was, axl?
Never seen him before.
Think you could describe him for a sketch artist?
Yeah. I got one of those photogenic memories.
the neighborhood.
Porn's a billion-dollar industry.
What? All i'm saying
is there's a lot of people who are ok with it.
You start knocking on doors across the street.
I'll get these.
You could use some tight-assed lube
yourself, sparky.
What am i supposed to do?
Just sit back and let this shitbag tank my career, too?
He's goddamn poison.
Kavanaugh's not my problem.
Oh, i am?
Pensions hasn't received your retirement paperwork.
I'm still sorting that out.
You were supposed to keep a low profile
so you could get out with a piece of your pension.
There's been a lot going on around here.
Phillips thinks too much is going on.
This came directly from the chief's office.
This puts my retirement effective immediately.
You take it now, the chief will see you get a piece of your pension.
Why now?
I had until my 15 mark.
Certain things are in motion.
This is a lifeline.
Sign this, and it'll save us all a lot of grief.
If you don't--
you can't cut me loose.
It's not my idea.
Brass is gonna be watching every move you make
You need me to make this place work.
I need people i can trust.
- So you won't help me fight this.
- You know a reason i should?
Quentin showed up at another clinic.
Unis spooked him. He's got hostages.
Who you're gonna trust with that?
All right, boys, here it is.
This guy's got a doctor, a mother
and her 3-month-old son
trapped in an examing room.
He's doused the doc and the mother with gasoline,
threatened to use them as kindling
if they didn't shut down all their methadone clinics.
Negotiator and swat's 30 minutes out.
Let's go. Shane, you coming?
Yeah. Yeah.
Shit.
needs to seal himself off.
in this place?
Get her out of here.
Get me a peeper scope.
I don't want anyone rattling this guy's cage.
I don't want anyone talking to him. Hey.
Are you with me?
Yeah.
'cause ronnie and i can take care of this.
I'm here, man. No, you're not.
I got innocents soaked with gasoline.
I need your head in the game.
It is. I promise. I'm ok.
Can i help you?
You have any idea where vic is?
We haven't seen him since lem's memorial.
No, i don't.
I saw him at the barn for a second. That's about it.
You think vic's staying here?
It crossed my mind.
He's not.
Sorry.
Ehi, tra Vic e me non c'e' nulla.
What about that thing in your arms?
Whatever shitpile you're cleaning up with your ex,
don't come dumping it on my doorstep.
And don't ever call my son a thing,
you uptight bitch.
I'm not uptight, sweetheart.
I'm a realist.
You have no idea what has been dumped
on your doorstep.
Vic. He is not gonna be there for him.
Well, i don't need anyone's help.
a full-time cop
and take care of this kid all by yourself?
that i won't be able to.
And what if they tell you that he's autistic, huh?
My son is fine.
They're all fine at first.
But we have 2 autistic kids,
and there's a genetic predisposition for siblings.
Maybe you're the one with the screwed-up genes.
Maybe. Maybe not. But keep your eyes open
because the sooner the doctors know, the more
they can do for him.
Mom and the doctor are jammed in the corner.
The baby's on a table by the door.
If we can get him to give up the kid,
swat can drop down between the junkie and the innocents.
I'll get an e.t.a. On swat and the negotiator.
Jesus christ. Don't hurt that little baby.
Stop! I'm gonna kill this goddamn baby, man.
Everybody just shut the hell up.
I'm gonna kill this goddamn thing.
Ehi, Quentin.
- Shane!
- Quentin!
Listen to me, man.
The reason the baby's crying is 'cause of the gasoline.
The fumes are probably burning his eyes.
What the hell's he doing?
You better get down here.
Just hand the kid over to me, get a little peace and quiet.
Just focus on what you got to do.
Who the hell are you, man?
I'm a cop.
What?
Shane vendrell. I'm unarmed.
Just hand over the crying kid
and take me instead.
A quiet detective is a much better bargaining chip, man.
Nah. It's a con.
You're full of shit. Just like everything else.
No, it's not a con. It's--
Quentin, listen to me. Open the door, buddy.
Quentin, open the door.
Look, ok. Look.
Look, buddy. You see?
You see?
Oh, my god.
Jesus christ, shane.
It's no con, man.
Get ready to move.
Any point you think i'm lying,
just...you just flick your bic, brother.
Ok?
Don't worry. I will, man.
Shit!
Quentin!
Quentin, listen to me, man.
Is there a closet in there or a cabinet or something?
Somewhere where the baby can breathe.
Yeah. I mean, it's--
good. Just put him in there and close the door, ok?
It keeps the fumes out of his eyes.
Shh.
Shh, shh. Shh, shh, shh.
I told you, quentin.
I told you, man, you can trust me.
I think this psycho's going for shane.
Right there.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
- Glad you put on a vest.
- Check the kid.
You wanna tell me what the hell happened back here?
We just saved 3 innocents from a homicidal junkie.
Maybe you could draw up the paperwork
and let me sign it.
Ahh!
- Aaaah! You lied.
- You lied to me.
You lied!
the sex shop this morning.
- Black, early 20s, earrings.
- Narrows things down.
I don't have anybody free.
Could you jump on this porn shop shooting?
Sounds titillating, but i'm still a little woozy.
That's what i get for trying to keep the peace, right?
Maybe you should go home.
I leave now it chews up one of my personal days.
I'm gonna hang and clean up some paperwork.
I'll be ok.
Thank god.
Circulate it to the skin joints, bookstores. See if he's a regular.
Ok.
Dmv didn't have any of the addresses
on the cousins of the el salvadoran we questioned
And i'm still waiting on i.n.s.
Good girl.
Good girl?
It's part of my new mentoring philosophy.
Right.
I thought you were meeting kavanaugh and picking up emolia.
Me, too. Sent me to the sewing shop.
It was closed. No one ever showed.
Vic said i should tell guardo
i was sorry for turning on him.
Offer up my handler asrestitucion.
He knew that guardo would wanna hurt the cop
that crushed his drug protection comeback.
Jesus. You told 'em it was lem.
They gave me the place, the time.
I set it up.
Told him it was a blond cop i've been working for.
You did this because vic threatened your son.
Said if i did it, he'd give me 500 bucks.
If i didn't,
that much.
What choice did i have?
You have the money?
No. He was supposed to drop it off at the
sewing shop yesterday. He never did.
I got scared.
Figured if he could off his own guy that way,
what's to stop him from killing me and my boy?
That's why she called me.
I got a man staying with her mother and with her son right now.
Yeah. I just want us all to be safe.
Far away from vic.
Phillips is on his way.
into more of these details.
You did fine.
Hey, uh, what happened to you?
I went to the sewing shop.
Oh, sorry about that.
Emolia moved the meeting place 3 times after i talked to you.
Where'd you finally meet her?
Behind sid's. Coffee place on wilton.
That place across from the 101 on-ramp?
I think so. I think so.
Ask emolia. She'd know.
- Anyway, no harm, no foul.
- Yeah.
Ow.
Easy. Ow! I know you're pissed at me.
I don't give a shit if i hear from you, ok?
I'll make it up to the kids.
Hope you have another bag of cash put aside
for the years of therapy they're gonna need.
- Don't say that.
- Cass is just like you.
- She internalizes everything.
- Hey.
You doing ok?
Yeah. I'll live,
as long as my ex isn't the one taking care of me.
- Hey, corrine.
- Hey.
We're gonna need an x ray of that shoulder.
Yeah.
How you feeling?
Good.
I still smell a little like diesel.
Just like ronnie's aftershave.
What the hell was that today?
I just saw a way to make your plan work.
My plan wasn't turning you into a duraflame.
I've had enough funerals for one week.
It was just my own little spin.
You can put another one in the win column,
though, right?
Listen, man.
We've all been beating ourselves up about lem.
But it's like you said, man.
It's nobody's fault.
- Except guardo's.
- Yeah.
Hey. Come here.
my retirement.
I'm not sure why, but i don't have much time.
- No, man.
- That's why you can't get reckless. You hear me?
I'm gonna need your help to finish this thing.
I can't lose you, too, shane.
You won't.
This doesn't add up.
The pieces fit. Motive, timing.
He's got a compelling case.
You and i both know vic is a cop with questionable ethics.
He capable of killing another cop? Maybe. But lem?
Her story's a little neat.
I'm at the last house on the d.e.a. List.
I knock. I definitely hear someone inside.
Maybe 2 people. They don't come to the door.
Then i get a call from kavanaugh
sending me off and running to the sewing shop?
Seems strange.
You think he's pushing the story?
Lying?
That doesn't fit either.
for his ex-wife
when any other cop in this building would have.
I know that look.
Something's not right
Chief wants vic on the retired list
before we file any charges.
He's not going without a fight.
What do you want me to do?
Stick to the guardo angle.
Bring vic in for questioning.
See what he has to say about emolia's story.
Ok.
I'm gonna head home now.
I might need to take that personal day tomorrow.
Oh, we'll try to fill the void.
Uh, vic.
You cruising for interns?
How's the shoulder?
Kevlar is my friend.
Kavanaugh's brought in a witness
to kill lem.
What witness?
Emolia melendez.
What's kavanaugh offering her?
Witness protection.
So you're here to arrest me?
- Right now i just need a statement.
- You think I did it?
Lem?
I need to take you back to the barn.
I can drive myself.
Ok. I'll see you back there.
Mackey's lawyer will paint her as a paid snitch,
for her testimony.
There's no evidence backing this story.
That's why i wanna continue this investigation.
This report is not complete yet.
What about wagenbach's el salvadoran suspect?
I've seen dutch cozy up to mackey.
I don't know where his loyalty lands.
We need to get him off this lemansky case.
We don't want another guy tipped off and on the run.
Ok.
I'll talk to wyms about him.
But this time if you can't keep it from becoming personal,
i'll go disciplinary on you, jon.
You'll lose those lt bars. You hear that?
I hear it.
Tell the chief he's got my word. Nothing personal.
What's this?
Requesting today's footage from the 101 freeway cam
at the wilton on-ramp
across from sid's coffee.
Just a hunch.
Any sign of vic?
Not yet.
Captain, a guy fitting the description of
our sex shop shooter
was seen in 4 other video stores today.
He bought out every copy of that.
I am not familiar with thedick 'n' grannyseries.
*************************
**************by holes and poles, inc.
- That the owner who got shot at?
- Yes.
- Not only is axl the producer, director, and distributor...
- but guess who's wearing the nixon mask.
*************************
***************political bent?
***************************
**********with your own smut?
It's my hook.
- I'm richard nixon and i'm dickin' granny.
- Yeah, we get it.
- Who's the old lady?
- Why? She's of age, right?
- Look, All my actors sign contracts--
- *********
************* every copy of that in the city.
Maybe he's a little upset about you dickin' granny.
Shit.
Number 3....
Forgot her name.
First-timer. She was raw.
But in the end, i always get a good performance.
We need a name and address.
It's vic.
Yeah.
Anyone ever tell you that you have incredibly expressive eyes?
Ever been on film?
Ever been in a mug book?
Family emergency. He can't come in right now.
He'll run out of emergencies,
then we'll get to the truth.
Hard to believe this place was ever a church.
We can track down axl's granny in the morning.
It's been a long day.
I'm ok. I'll wait for the address and follow it up tonight.
It's your first week. You can't keep up this kind of pace.
Now, i'm just talking general health.
You got to take care of yourself.
******** these pews?
Of course.
Phillips paid me a visit today.
If i don't turn this place around
before the quarterly statistics come out,
they might be saying mass down there again real soon.
I'm captain wyms. Sorry to disturb you so late,
ma'am. You know this man?
Edmond!
Stop!
Stop! Drop the gun!
Drop that gun.
Drop the gun.
Please, kid, just drop the gun.
Please don't make me shoot you.
- Drop the gun, asshole, or i will shoot.
- Edmond, don't!
Drop the gun, goddamn it!
- Do it now!
- Drop the gun.
Get on your knees.
- Why did you do it, grandma?
- Get ****************** right now!
How could you let that man do that to you?
He got arrested for stealing a car 6 months ago.
I neede his bail money.
You shouldn't have done it, grandma.
Why'd you be his whore?
What are you doing here?
You got emolia to lie for you.
Now you know the difference between a lie and a truth?
You think i'm a cop killer.
Maybe i am.
You're a cop.
Right?
That sounds like a direct threat on my life,
detective. You know what that means?
It means you just stepped
onto an entirely new playing field.
And for your sake,
i hope you know the rules of the game.
That it? You came all the way down here
just to blow words by me?
It's a street tactic.
Always let the bad guy know you're on to his game.
Makes him change tact so he makes mistakes.
Then i guess i should let you know
****************    of curtis lemansky.
There are unis at your house,
and they're waiting to bring you in.
Gabino Guiz?
This is the address i.n.s. Gave me for the cousin.
Nobody home. What a shock. Let's go.
Oh, that's gross.
Dutch. Bloody cat prints.
Crime scene. Tread lightly.
6- paul-32 requesting 4 additional units
and csu
at 89 san marcos.
I've got multiple 187s,
3, possibly 4...
you got to be shitting me.
- They're asleep.
- I just didn't feel like going home.
I'm sorry i dropped out this week.
They just need to hear your voice.
- What is it?
- K*********************
with lem's death.
Oh, my god. That's ridiculous.
He got some low-life c.i. To lie for him.
What are you gonna do?
i'll get right to it.
Last year captain rawling initiated an inquiry
into the farmington gang and drug unit.
Supervised by lieutenant kavanaugh...
from i.a.d., this department conducted
a 7-month investigation...
- Daddy!
- Get out! Go back in your room right now!
I'm sorry. I just didn't want her to see.
...., he fled justice,
became a wanted fugitive.
No doubt the thought of spending years in prison
was a frightening proposition.
We'll never know what triggered
detective lemansky's reluctance to....
serve his time. Because less than
24 hours later, he was found brutally murdered.
Someone dropped a live grenade
in the front seat of his car.
That murder investigation is ongoing
and as of yet no suspects are in custody.
***************************
*********************friends and family.
But within this tragedy, there is a message,
and one that i hope will shake
this department to its core.
Breaking the law and wearing a badge
is a dangerous combination,
and this city will not tolerate it.
This department will not tolerate it.
It's the primary objective of this police council
over the next 18 months
to squash corruption within our own ranks.
And cops involved in any illegal activities
will be rooted out.
They will be relieved of duty
and prosecuted to the full extent of the law,
just as detective curtis lemansky was being prosecuted
for his corrupt actions.
- You son of a bitch.
- This community needs police officers...
who are peaceful and trustworthy civil servants.
It's our goal to return dignity
and respect to the badge...
And to the men and women who wear one
a reason to be proud.
Nothing personal.
Synch: Klonni, Javawarrior2003, ::Emicad::
Transcript: SW
[www.subway.fr]
::Italian Subs Addicted::
[www.italiansubs.net]