Previously on "The Shield"...
Shane?
We're going to find out who did this,
and we're gonna kill him.
- Grenades?
- The el salvadorans. Start there.
It's Guardo.
He stepped on his protection plate twice.
Nydia Hernandez? We have information that
someone is planning on kidnapping you.
Well, I should call Guardo and warn him.
No, no, no. We don't know who's
listening on this side of the line.
We have to move you now.
- Come on. We better get going.
- Ok.
What's this?
It's the message I'm waiting on from Guardo.
A necklace.
You tell him that if he ever wants
to see her again,
He has 24 hours to get 50 grand
in person to L.A.
Guardo wanted to have you killed.
You made up a story about Vic so that
you could get witness protection.
Now, does that sound about right?
I fed her the story.
I framed him. Guilty man.
You're under arrest for interfering
with police business under call of authority.
- Case against Vic has been dropped.
- This has turned into a kidnapping.
- Just let Nydia go.
- She's how we're going to get to Guardo.
For every second he gets to breathe,
and Lem doesn't, is unacceptable.
So how come no one's helping you?
Helping me watch you?
I think I can handle it.
- No calls.
- I need to talk to Guardo.
The wrong people could be listening.
You could say something that could reveal
your location on a listen.
I talk to him everyday.
He'll get worried if I don't call.
He might lower his guard if you do.
For all we know, this could be an inside threat.
Until we know more, the less he knows
or hears, the safer it'll be.
Besides, he's probably going to
call you at some point.
When he's alone.
Right?
Yeah.
Well, then we'll wait for that call.
Corrine. Hi.
- Is everything all right?
- Yeah. Look, I know it's early,
but I've been meaning to drop off
these hand-me down toys for jackson.
- Mara's expecting them.
- Yeah. Come on in.
- Ahh. Look at him.
- I appreciate this.
- I don't want them to go to waste, so...
- They won't. Trust me.
Mara's not in the house,
so daddy's stepping up.
- Um, I heard Vic was cleared of all the charges.
- Yeah.
Kavanaugh planted that evidence
in Vic's apartment. Set the whole thing up.
I had the door on, when I, um,
told him about all that extra money.
I kept my mouth shut.
- I don't know, maybe Lem...
- Sweetie, no. Lem's not your fault.
If it's anybody's, it's Kavanaugh's.
And you didn't screw up.
You know, he crossed a line.
What's going to happen to Vic now?
- Oh, he's in the clear.
- He's not himself.
Yeah. Well, how can any of us be?
He's looking for the person
who killed Lem, right?
He has to be.
What happens if he finds him?
I lost one of my closest and
most dearest friends.
- I'm not going to lose him, too.
- He's always been there.
The kids, they're so connected to him.
Now it feels like all that's changed.
It hasn't changed.
It won't. I won't let it.
Promise.
- Why am I trusting you?
- If you care about Guardo,
You'll play it my way. Otherwise, you'll
lead him right to this killer Salceda.
- I never even heard of Salceda.
- There's no reason you would.
He wants Guardo's business.
He'll eliminate him to get it.
Guardo's strong.
Nobody can get to him.
Not even the cartel?
Salceda's mexican.
You really think anybody's going to
complain when a salvadoran gets replaced
by one of their own?
- Guardo can take care of himself.
- Maybe I should let him do that then.
Your boyfriend gets killed, it's
one less piece of shit I have to scoop up.
One more murder notch for Salceda.
Where you going?
- The bathroom.
- Fine.
Leave the phone.
Uh, the guy's the store manager.
The other 2 are pharmacy tech and a cashier.
- Looks fresh.
- Suspects came in as soon as the doors opened,
those 2 were the only ones in the place.
Took the employees in the back, shot'em, and
then cleared the ephedrine out of this locked case.
- It's not the most original crime in the world.
- Meth heads.
You know, shred 'em.
Wanting to plan this much on destruction.
- That's one theory.
- You got another?
Used to be these smash and grabs
were just users wanting a fix.
Now, that ephedrine's so locked down,
just as likely to be cookers
needing ingredients.
Yeah, well, in either case we're waiting
for the owner to come down
and then we'll see how much they got.
That's second multiple murder in a week.
Wonder what the brass is going to think
about my body count.
Would be nice to close it.
Spoken like a true captain.
Hey, Dutch?
- I owe you an apology.
- For what?
For not embracing this partnership sooner.
The truth is, we're on the verge of becoming
a damn good team.
Well, I'm still making up my mind.
Well, if you think about it, your weaknesses
are my strength, and Viceversa.
And, uh, what exactly are
my weaknesses, Steve?
Arrogance,
overconfidence, the inability to give
credit to those around you.
- Come on. I'm not tellin'ya anything you don't already know.
- Anything else?
You're afraid Cardera was the better detective
and you were just drafting off of her,
so you treat me like a piece of shit
because if we start tanking,
you can paint me as the guy
that dragged you down.
Hey, you asked.
Got me rattlin' this whole plan.
Right out of my head.
And I think we should just step back
from this whole thing.
Just from the girlfriend,
just for a little while.
- Step back.
- You were just cleared. We were all in the clear
for the first time in a very long time, man.
Lettin' Lem's death go unanswered
isn't being in the clear.
Besides, the night is in play.
We're down the road.
Tell 'em we found the guy who's trying
to kill Guardo.
We'll put a little distance
between us and her.
Wait for Guardo to get back in the country.
That's when we make our move, in a month or two.
Guardo killed Lem or knows who did.
I'm not scheduling payback for
later in the year.
I'm just talking about lettin'
the dust settle, man.
The public doesn't want this case solved
because it opens old wounds.
Now, they hung Lem out to the press
as a dirty cop.
That makes us the only ones
who care enough to make it right.
They got nowhere on the investigation.
Now Claudette's assigning it to new cases.
We owe it to Lem.
It's on us.
Guardo might call anytime.
Go back to the Barn.
Try to get us some heavier firepower.
We might need it.
I'm supposed to have the day off.
What if Claudette asks?
Just picking up more of Lem's stuff.
Let's get this straight.
We need the truth.
This thing's going to get a lot uglier
before it gets better.
Shooters. Let's call 'em early 30s.
Doesn't look like they're tweaking.
Make copies of this, gave it to all the units.
Owner thinks they got away with
some soap and ephedrine.
Couple of white guys. One of them has tats.
See if they're arians, bikers, one of them.
- Something else?
- This feels like a strike team case to me.
Drug world. Why not hand it off to them
and put me back on the Lemansky murder?
- I thought you hit a dead-end there?
- Looks like Guardo's out of the country,
but a name keeps popping up in
my interviews. Hernan.
- Hernan. Connected?
- Don't know. But several salvadorans mentioned him.
It's like a ghost. Leads me to believe he's either
got something to hide, he's smart, or both.
The strike team's been on the sideline
since Lemansky's death.
If you hear something on Hernan,
let me know.
Otherwise, try to clear this
pharmacy murder quick.
- You two still work here?
- Taking some personal days. Sent you the memo.
- What about you?
- I used mine up on the wisdom teeth.
- As long as you're still on the clock, I need you.
- I'll just put these on the truck.
- Just came by to get some things of Lem's.
- Saves me having to ask.
We're short of lockers. I'm going to need his
when it's ready.
- I'll have it cleared out by tomorrow.
- How's Vic doing?
- He lost a friend.
- I understand.
- He still hasn't returned my calls.
- Well, he's been off-duty.
As soon as he can, I want him back at work
and I don't mean on the Lemansky killing either.
- You don't have to worry about that.
- Good. And...
if he thinks he can avoid my warnings by
ducking calls, tell him as far as I'm concerned,
he just got it.
- Have Ronnie find me.
- Hey, Dutch!
I don't know what this tattoo is,
but it doesn't match anything on the books.
Not arian nation.
Looks like some kind of bird.
Can't i.d. the tats.
Might be gang, but I doubt it.
Ronnie.
This is one of the suspects
in the pharmacy shooting.
- You know him?
- No.
What about the tattoo?
Military. Navy, I think.
A lot of these assholes first get
hooked up on it for Uncle Sam.
Armed forces second only to the joint
as a recruitment center.
Stay with this one with
Dutch and Steve.
We got 3 dead already.
I want them before they need more supplies.
Ok.
I don't need another person to baby-sit.
You were the one that said this
was a strike team case.
You got your wish.
Besides, keep your ears open,
if Mackey and Vendrell are looking for
Lemansky's killer, like I think they are,
- might get one of it through Ronnie. Let me know.
- Ok.
Answer it.
- Hello?
- Nydia?
- Give me that back!
- I need to talk to him.
Please. Just for a minute.
You said you wanted to protect him.
To save his life, right?
You got to do things my way.
Remember?
Talk.
You know who I am, asshole?
She's still alive. For now.
That's the last time
you get to hear her voice.
You're a gringo. Who's this?
Are you mob? Russian?
I'm the guy that decides
whether Nydia lives or dies.
And who her last lover is.
- You touch her, you're dead.
- Oh, you got that all turned around.
If I don't see you with
the money, she dies.
But not until she feels
my soft touch.
Stupid bitch.
Next word out of your mouth
better be 'when'.
Or I will rape and kill that
bitch while you're listening.
When?
Where are you?
Near the border.
MacArthur Park.
The trash can by the lake.
Southeast corner. You got that?
Yeah.
How soon can you be there?
- Tomorrow. Maybe the next day.
- I know your business.
You protect things.
What do you think the cartel's
going to think when they find out
you can't even protect
your own personal piece of ass?
- I can be there in 3 hours.
- Come alone.
Once I know I got the 50 grand,
I'll let you know where you can find the girl.
You don't come by yourself, she dies
and your protection business
along with her.
- All right. We're on. Did you bring that back-up?
- Yeah,
but I lost Ronnie.
He blew through his goddamn
personal days on his teeth.
We're meeting with Guardo in 3 hours.
Just because Guardo's coming
doesn't mean he's not going
to try to set us up, too.
We'll go to the drop-off point early.
Make sure there's no trap.
I have a call into an
agent Jordan Zinman
About a salvadoran named Hernan.
It's important. He may be a material witness
in the murder of a policeman.
Ok. Just tell him I called.
Give it to him.
Just followed my military hunch.
Checked navy records of guys
who lost their benefits
for felony conViction
against known L.A. Residents.
- Slide it over the fence.
- We can wrap this up by dinner.
The only thing bigger than Wym's body
count's going to be our closure rate.
No access to the back, so go
around the side, cover the rear.
- You ready?
- Everyone stay behind me.
Tommy, is that you?
I have an arrest warrant for
Tom Franklin. Is he here?
- Oh, jesus christ.
- Is he here?!
- What is this?
- House is clear.
Where is he?
He works out in the garage a lot.
Maybe back there.
Let's go. Coming out!
Go there!
Not here.
Dry ice. No fumes.
All right. We're clear.
- Who are you?
- His sister.
- Lisa.
- You know your brother was cooking meth out here?
- Said he was fixing up an old car.
- Did you see him this morning?
- He was gone before I woke up.
- How can we find him?
- Your brother killed 3 people today.
- Oh.
If he's not here,
who's going to take care of me?
If Guardo's been in Mexico,
- what if he was there when Lem died?
- He ordered it and he knows who did it.
- How are we going to know that for sure?
- He'll give that up for his life.
- Nydia comfortable in the van?
- She's excited about her big reunion.
You gonna check on her?
Just don't want her
getting too curious.
Guardo's still 2 hours out.
We'll do a head count now.
See if the population gets any browner
over the next couple of hours.
Corinne came by this morning.
Brought some toys for jackson.
But she really came by because
she's worried about you.
About what you're going to do.
Where that leaves the kids.
She mention the kids?
Yeah.
When we finish up with Guardo,
I'll drop by.
Maybe we should check on the girl.
Tom Franklin's sister...
Won't or can't give up her brother.
- Any idea on the other suspect?
- Not yet.
- Hello, sergeant. Welcome back.
- Thanks.
- We got another pharmacy robbery on western.
- Anyone hurt?
Just medicine cabinets. Took all
the ephedrine in the store.
Get out there, see what you can find.
Here we go.
Claudette?
- This is Skip Osaka.
- Hi.
Department hired him to take some
publicity pictures of personnel.
I thought the department
had that handled already.
You know, why don't you get started.
Your pass gives you full access.
Thanks. Is there someplace I can
set up my equipment?
Pick an open desk.
After Lemansky, they thought it was a
good idea the department get some good PR
We both want this place to survive, so
I made sure the Barn gets its shot, too.
The only good publicity I need
is lower crime stats.
This campaign won't hurt.
Now, as a reservist, they want
some pictures of me
in uniform, as well.
Maybe some of you, too.
I'll work with him.
You see the 2 carloads?
- They circled twice. They're hard to miss.
- We need an army, Vic.
With the shit these guys might
be packing, I'm talking literally.
I still don't know if Guardo's in town.
We'll wait and make sure.
He rounded all the employees
and customers up
and brought 'em to the back, and
then broke into the drug cabinets.
He only took the ephedrine. Left everything else.
He didn't even try the register.
Just like this morning. Who's this?
That's Leticia Everett.
She's the assistant manager.
Good job.
Hi, Leticia.
Is this the man that robbed you?
- One of them.
- What did the other guy look like?
He was a white guy, too. Kind of looked
like that one. They could've been brothers.
You see the girl that came in?
Are these the same guys that killed
those other people this morning?
Maybe.
- Why didn't they kill us?
- Stick around, ok? We may need you a little more.
- It's pretty crowded in here.
- Yeah. Probably didn't have enough bullets.
I need to take this.
- Yeah?
- He's good.
Broke the thing damn open.
- Hey, you still on that Claudette thing?
- Hip-deep.
I've been trying to get in touch
with our mexican federali
see if Guardo's really crossing
the border or not.
- You on a wire connection?
- No, I'm in the middle of something.
Man. I'm in a real vacuum here. Can't you
break away for a couple of seconds?
- When I can, I will.
- All right.
- Let me know when things free up.
- Ok.
Gardocki.
Thanks.
Anything interesting?
Tom Franklin came home.
Unis grabbed him up
and they're taking him
to the barn.
Hey!
Your buddy's got all the ephedrine,
left you holding the bill.
He's got a knack for
avoiding the cameras.
So all we got is you
committing armed robbery
and 3 dead bodies.
The Berkley law grads and the D.A.'s office
are going to be tearing
each other's eyes out
to get this case.
What if I said he killed
those people?
Well, that's, uh...that's a start. I'd
like to think that's the truth here.
He's my cousin.
Bobby.
It was his idea.
He made a deal with some dude in
the horde to cook up 20 pounds of meth.
We never made that much before.
Bobby knew some mexican who was
going to get us the ephedrine from over there.
- What happened?
- He showed up with a bunch of plants.
- So ephedrine goes wild down there.
- What the hell are we supposed to do with plants?
- So you started killing people?
- I told Bobby to back out of the deal.
But he got paid in advance,
blew most of his money
on a harley and some new pussy.
- And left you out to dry with the horde.
- No shit.
Ripping up those pharmacies was
the only shot we had
to cook up enough shit in time.
But I didn't know he was going to
kill those people, 'til I heard the shot.
How do we find him?
His new pussy lived in Van Nuys.
If he's anywhere, he's
messing up the sheets with her.
- Yeah?
- We got him.
- Stay here.
- Again?
For your own safety, ok?
Trust me? Stay down.
Just like a bee to honey.
- You got the money?
- Yeah.
- He's got 2 guys between us and him.
- Luckily I don't give a shit about the cash.
He knows he's got the heat on him
so he's got a safe place to stay
until this thing is done.
- Well, what if he's not there alone?
- He's worried about his reputation.
He's going to make sure
he gets to those kidnappers.
The more guys he puts staking out
the money, the better his chances are.
- Well, I've still got Nydia in the truck.
- Take her back home.
I'll follow Guardo back to his hole.
I figure we've got a half-hour before
his guys start to get suspicious.
Just call me when you get the location.
- If there's time.
- I'm serious.
Don't make a move until I can be there
to back you up, all right?
Just get the girl back.
- Found Guardo.
- That's a relief.
Last chance.
I could use you.
We're on a stakeout now. The guy
should be showing up anytime.
- Our window's closing. I'll call you later.
- Ok. Be sure and do that.
Everything ok?
Be a lot better if Bobby showed up.
How's... How's Vic doing,
by the way?
He's ok. I talked to him yesterday.
He's...
- dealing with things his own way.
- Sure.
I was the first one to see
the holes in Kavanaugh's story.
Let's get ready to move.
Turn around, asshole.
That's him. Move. Move!
Hey!
Get off of him!
Hey, hey, hey!
Roll over.
Now you'll roll over.
- Hold still, asshole.
- Get up!
Right there!
Right there.
Officer.
You're not going to find
anything here.
I found what I want.
Nydia?
I brought the money.
I did what you said.
You leave your guys at the park
as a welcome wagon?
Too bad. You could have
used them.
What happened?
Where's Guardo? Your friend?
Salceda was hiding at
Guardo's place. Vic's taking him in.
So where's Guardo?
You said he was back in town.
Well, I guess the rumor was just that.
Good news is Salceda believed it.
- He fell right into our trap.
- So, he's safe? We're safe again?
Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, good luck.
Don't judge me.
I'm not.
It's just, um...
I'm pregnant.
A month.
I haven't told Guardo yet.
That's why I quit smoking.
Just thought that if I hadn't
it would hurt the baby, right?
No.
I just want my baby
to know his father.
Yeah.
We recovered the stolen ephedrine
from the house, and the murder weapon.
Music to my ears.
Ron, you did a great job out there.
He trusts the instincts of
the people he works with.
So, i guess we're done, right?
Let's get back out there.
What about the horde?
What about them?
Well, the cousins are still supposed
to give them the meth, right?
There is no meth.
We're not going to make a deal on a trio
of homicides just to get us some dealers.
Wait.
The horde doesn't know there's no meth.
Bobby's the contact,
say we offered them leniency for
his cousin who wasn't the shooter.
- Maybe they'd go for it.
- He killed 3 people.
Let's just turn it over to the D.A.
The horde's an impossible crew to crack
because nobody wants to be the enemy, right?
We could bust them in a lot of ways.
And if they don't get what they want,
they're just going to find another cooker,
won't they?
We'll use Bobby.
Go through the exchangeas planned.
The horde doesn't know what Tom looks like,
so we'll give them you instead.
What do you want?
I can get the money back.
10 times that.
Take me to a police station.
I won't say anything without a lawyer.
What do you want?
You killed my friend a week ago.
You tossed a grenade in his car.
Blew his guts out.
I don't know anything about that.
I want to know how you found him.
Who led you to him?
It wasn't me.
Then you know who did it
because you gave the order.
Where's Nydia?
- Did you harm her?
- His name was Curtis Lemansky.
He was a good cop.
He was my friend and you killed him.
All i want is to hear you say it.
I've been in Mexico for 2 weeks.
I wasn't near no cop getting killed.
- Your friend is making a mistake.
- You're going to tell me how he got killed
or you're going to tellme who did it. Either way,
you're not leaving this place until i know every detail.
I don't know anything.
I told you.
Maybe Nydia can help you
remember something.
Don't hurt her.
Don't make us hurt her, man.
Just tell him what he wants to know.
Get her undressed.
All right!
It was Lino. Lino prieto.
You gave him the order.
I didn't give any order.
I heard about it in Mexico.
My people were pissed off.
Asshole brought a lot of shit down
on us without getting exemption.
How'd he find my guy?
Ask him.
Prieto is the ones hould be hanging here.
Not me.
If you're telling the truth, he will be.
- Yeah?
- Pull up everything you've got on Lino Prieto.
I'm on it now.
- What happened to Guardo?
- He's at the place with Shane.
- What'd he say?
- He had nothing to do with it.
That this guy Prieto went off the grid
and acted on his own.
Did you need something?
- Yeah, it's time to go.
- I'll be right there.
- Desk boy still hounding you?
- Yep.
If Shane's with him, how'she going to meet you?
Flying solo on this one.
1731 Charles street.
Apartment 6.
Why don't you wait? Wait, i'll get
freed upon this, and i'll meet you.
Can't slow down.
Call me later.
Sorry to keep everybody waiting.
I'm a cop.
Lino Prieto?
I'm his brother, Roberto.
Let me see some I.D.
Right now. Come on.
Where's your brother at?
He's in jail.
Jail.
Since when?
Been almost a month.
I told you, Lino ain't here.
That's his wife, Margie,
these are his kids.
So, your brother goes to jail and you
come over here to keep his wife company?
I came over to check on them,
that's all.
Guardo Lima says that your brother
killed a friend of mine.
A cop.
- Guardo's a lying asshole.
- Doesn't mean it's not true.
My brother was stupid to get in it again,
but he wouldn't kill anybody.
What's he in lock-up for?
Got drunk, stole a car,
crashed it into a store.
Why would Guardo give me
your brother's name?
They were tight once. They ran together. One day Guardo's
girlfriend told him she thought my brother was handsome.
You keep this visit to yourself,
you'll never see me again.
Maybe they won't show.
Not likely.
Not like Ronnie.
He's quiet.
There's something there.
Wouldn't mind doing a little
strike team time myself.
Fall into the shit,
get the blood moving.
Yeah.
It's too bad you get those headaches.
You know, you're very sarcastic.
I forgot to list that one.
You ready to hear a little
constructive criticism yourself?
Are you kidding me?
I don't need that kind of head trip.
Got 3 bikers coming in.
What's going on?
- Who's that?
- Tom.
My cousin.
You are hard to reach.
You got a problem?
You want a lot of shit, man.
It takes time to cook it up.
So, let's see it.
You know, if this works out,
we can make this a regular thing.
Hands! Hands!
Move in. Move in. Move in.
- I got 'em.
- Get down. Turn around.
- Don't move!
- Easy, man.
Turn around.
Turn around!
Get there.
- Spread 'em! Spread 'em.
- Don't move.
All clear.
We got 'em all.
Nice operation. Thanks for making
me look good to the captain.
Way to go, Billy.
Thanks.
No biggie. Hey.
Hey, great job out there.
You were the one with the idea
of taking down the horde.
Guess the tutoring is paying off.
So, when's the next lesson?
I got a little more to do here, but if
you want to stick around, i'll be here.
Ok.
I got to go. Can you and Billy
cover me on the paperwork?
- Uh, i guess.
- Thanks. I owe you one. Good work today.
Good job.
Hey.
Let me go.
Please.
Shut up, shit head.
I didn't do it.
I swear.
He's got the wrong guy.
Yeah.
I know.
Lino Prieto did it, right?
I came in from the gang.
You could take down the whole crew.
I didn't kill that cop.
Yeah, well you killed a shit-load
of other people.
What about that little backyard barbeque
you and your boys blew up? Huh? Huh?
Those were kids, man. Your grenades blew
holesin them that i could goddamn see through.
I had to walk through their blood.
Money.
I give you money.
I make you rich.
What do you want?
Peace.
I know you'reinterested.
I wouldn't be here if you
were a straight-up cop.
Tell him i escaped.
You could retire tomorrow.
Sorry, man.
I don't like the way blood money spends.
Nydia's pregnant.
Thought you should know
she's going to have your kid.
Lino prieto's been in jail
for the last 3 1/2 weeks.
- Come on, Vic, man.
- So all i got is you.
How'd you find my guy?
Was it Emolia?
Kavanaugh? How?
- I'm going to get to the truth.
- I didn't do it!
I didn't... Aah!
Get anything from gardocki?
Nothing specific.
Couple of phone calls he
didn't want me to hear.
Could have been anything, really.
How are you adjusting
working with billings?
It's fine.
It's just not the same, that's all.
How's your mystery salvadoran?
Hernan. Nothing.
But now i'm free to look for him.
Um, when we were partners,
i pulled my weight, right?
I mean, you never felt like you were
carrying me or anything, did you?
You made me a better detective.
You'll make billings one, too.
Yeah. Yeah.
Hey. Hey.
Just tell me what i want
to know and this'll be over.
Your boss was involved?
Come on, man. He's not talking.
He will.
He'll talk!
Who was it?
Did a black cop get in touch with you?
Kavanaugh?
David Aceveda?
It was Emolia, wasn't it?
It was that salvadorian slut
that tipped you off. I know it.
You know, maybe he didn't do it, man.
- If it wasn't Guardo, who was it?
- Look at him, man.
If he had a name, don't you think
he would have told us by now?
- That just means he was acting alone.
- This is crazy, man.
He killed Lem!
Don't you remember his body, his face?
Do you think you can
just forget that? Huh?
Don't you think he deserves
to die for what he did?
Look, i'm asking you
not to do this for me.
Why not?
Look, he's got money.
I mean, a hell of a lot
more than that ransom.
- He offered me some to let him go.
- You'd put a price on Lem's life?
No, man. Come on.
No! But it always comes
down to the same thing.
Our families. Our futures.
Taking care of all that.
We will. I'm glad your friend died.
Hey, hey, listen to me. Listen to me.
Look, you kill him,
you kill him, you cut off our
chance of ever finding out the truth.
I want every single person who had a
hand in this to suffer, not just Guardo.
Thank you.
You were right.
If he had a real name to
tell us, he would have.
He acted alone.
So, what now?
We make sure this body never gets found.
As long as Guardo's at large, he'll always
remain the primary suspect in Lem's death.
We just killed somebody.
Detective work isn't as sexy,
but it's where brain power like
yours really gets utilized.
And one of the things you should
start doing is making a library.
Copy interesting cases, things
you don't want to forget.
Take them home. Organize them in a way
you can look through them occasionally.
- Yeah, that's really smart.
- Train your brain.
Always be asking questions.
Think like a detective about
everything in your life,
- every second.
- And you have
something like that? A library?
I compiled a couple folders over the
last decade. Pictures, notes, theories.
Keep 'em. I'll show them to
you some time, if you want.
Give you an idea how to organize it.
It's still early.
We could order some chinese food.
I've got a big bottle of wine
i've been waiting to open.
What?
Is this a date?
Uh, i don't know. Do you want it to be?
- Do you have a girlfriend or something?
- No. No. Why?
Because there's a woman
on your porch watching us.
- Stay here.
- Dutch, i'm a cop.
Just give me a second.
- Can i help you?
- I'm agent Zinman.
I.c.e. Left me a message.
- You have information about Hernan?
- Can you lose your date?
Hernando's undercover in
the salvadoran organization.
He's infiltrated that group deeper
than anyone in the federal system.
I can't compromise his position.
I don't want to compromise anything.
I just want to ask him a few questions.
Find another intel source
and stop trying to contact him.
I don't think so.
A cop was killed by the salvadorans.
You say your guy is inside?
I'm going to need to talk to him to get
the information i need to solve this case.
I know you're investigating
the murder of a police officer
and you're looking for Guardo Lima,
but he didn't commit that crime.
He, uh... He undercover, too?
According to Hernando, he was out
of the country when it happened.
I know he was out of the country.
It doesn't mean he didn't order it.
Killer used a grenade.
That's Guardo's calling card.
Guardo is back in los angeles.
According to Hernan,
it would take something very
important to bring him out of hiding.
Focus your effort there,
but leave Hernan out of it.
Can i use him to find Guardo?
No. Hernan is way too valuable
to the federal government.
This isn't a pissing contest.
It's an order.
Guy ever clean this thing out?
It's like being back in high school.
Hey. Remember when he took that?
Disposable. He took from that dealer.
- Last shot.
- Almost got the case thrown out.
Tampering with evidence. Shit.
- Here, you take it.
- I don't need it.
Looks like you do.
Look who's here. How you doin'?
Just had my first good
night's sleep in a while.
Just tell me where you need me.
You still have a few days of
personal time left, don't you?
Don't need 'em. Just looking
forward to getting back in the shit.
I'll be glad to accommodate.
- Whose jacket?
- It's Kevin Hyatt.
He used to be a rising star in i.n.s.
When homeland security took over, he
thought the room got a little crowded.
Department's had him for over a year.
He's ours starting next week.
I'll look over it, but
you're not adding anybody to my
team that i don't have approval of.
He's not your addition.
He's your replacement.
You only got a month left before
you're 50 and you retire, right?
Unless my math's wrong.
I need you to get him up to speed.
- A lot can happen in a month.
- True enough.
Hyatt sounds like a solid
guy. Give him a call.
I really need you to help
him with his transition.
Well, like i said, wherever you need me.
Transcript: SW
[www.subway.com]
Synchro: Pasbel, ::emicad::, Javawarrior2003
:: Italian Subs Addicted::
[www.italiansubs.net]