Previously on The Shield...
He screwed my ex wife
with the sole purpose
of making this investigation
seem like a personal vendetta.
This guy's just pissing,he's
pissing all over us.
- I've made you coffee and I've been patient,
- you need to go.
Just stop, stop. Stop!
- I'm gonna take a deal.
- I report for processing tomorrow morning.
We gotta wait for you to get to mexico.
We got money parked in an account for you.
- It's all set up.
- I'm not going that route.
They're gonna make you give us up.
Why'd you even come back here tonight
if you weren't planning on leaving?
Shane?
We're gonna find out who did
this. And we're gonna kill him.
It's Guardo, he stepped
on his protection twice.
Killing lem was a message to stay away.
You've murdered two of
your own team members.
- You're done with Mackey. You're off of it.
- I have proof that Vic had lemansky killed.
I say that Vic used me as a middle
man to set up the hit on his guy.
I'm just trying to get
you to tell the truth.
It's just somebody
else's truth, that's all.
You get emolia to lie for you. You just
stepped onto an entirely new playing field.
I hope you know the rules of the game.
Sorry. Claudette had us running down a
lead on the san marcos house slaughter.
I thought that was robbery/homicide.
They'd get their loafers dirty knocking
on doors. Who's the bag of bones?
Jupo nunez. Founding father
of the salvadoran gang.
Granted parole yesterday after
50 years of a life sentence.
- Why the early release?
- He's terminal.Lung cancer.
Hey.
You think you can hang on long
enough to answer a few questions?
- Do I know you?
- Vic Mackey.You're before my time.
But your male nurse
probably heard of me.
He's the farmington cop, grandpa.
Had the run-ins with Guardo.
You're the one raging war against us.
Come to tear down a dying man?
My beef's with Guardo.
He calls the shots now.
I built this gang from the ground up.
Guardo, all of them,owe me everything.
Leaving you here to live in
paradise. After a lifetime of service.
That's one hell of a pension plan.
You came here to insult me?
I came here to give you a chance
to salvage your life's work.
Now you give me Guardo.
I turn on one of my
own,I disgrace myself.
The salvadoranslost their
honor after Guardo killed a cop.
You old school guys. You
knew never to do that.
And in return, we showed
you a level of respect.
Giving him up is a step towards
restoring the glory days.
- I don't know he killed one of you.
- We do. Besides,
maybe your new leader would
have a better sense of history.
How to treat their heroes.
The new generation. No
respectfor the rules.
That's disgraceful.
What's worse is kids
like your grandson here
are gonna have to pay the
price for that disrespect.
That gat he's hiding under
his shirt, that's a felony.
Who knows what else I might
find if I decide to bea hardass.
Guardo killed danny rosa.
All I have is a number.
It's where we call him
to give him a message.
Vic, it's asher.
- what's going on?
- I'm at your house.Serving a search warrant.
- For what?
- I don't know.
- Well, who's there?
- kavanaugh,wagenbach, captain wyms.
Is there anything you need me
to do? Anything to clean up?
No. There's nothing to find.
Thanks for the heads up though.
Jesus christ, kavanaugh's at my
place. He's got a search warrant.
Based on the emolia's bullshit story?
Hey, hey. Is there something
that I need to know?
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
Is there anything there to find?
- About lem or anything else?
- No.
Nothing in Vic's closet. You?
Just leftovers.
Did you lookin the trash?
You see the brand new jacket?
Garbage is what god made unis for.
I thought you were gonna
take a personal day.
It's thursday. I figured I take
it tomorrow. Get the 3-day weekend.
Check the bathroom,would you?
Claudette!
Claudette.
- Yeah.
- Found this balled up in the trash. The circle there is
where portillo autobody is.
- Where lemansky was killed.
- Yeah.
Mackey said he'd never been there.
Just keep looking. Cause if he's
this sloppy, maybe there's more.
You've read the statement.
You swear it's entirely truthful,
everything about detective Mackey?
- Yes.
- Ok. Sign and date here.
Finished the search of
Vic's house and found these.
This is a matchbook from tama's costora.
Where emolia's been working.
Vic said he hadn't seen or spoken to
her since he cut her off as an informant.
Of course, we don't know when
he picked up the matchbook.
$500 cash tucked
inside his yellow pages.
Exact amount that emolia said Vic
offered to give lem up to Guardo.
Vic or any of the other
guys return our calls?
Not yet.
- Was the cash loose in the phone book?
- No. It was in that envelope.
Send it to the crime lab. See if
you can get Vic's prints off of it.
Fine. But if you ask
me,this is all bullshit.
There's no way Vic offed
one of his own guys.
Phone number tracks
here. Nydia hernandez.
I knocked.No one answered.
So what now?
We're gonna go inside. Wait for
Guardo. Take him someplace private.
Find out how he got close to lem.
Then we're gonna kill him.
And anybody else involved.
all units stand by for crime broadcast.
Wanted for questioning,detective Vic Mackey.
Farmington detectives.Requesting any
information on his current location.
- All units...
- They must have found something in your house.
- There was nothing to find.
- Why else would they issue an apb?
Look, why don't we just go back to
the barn, see what the hell they found,
and clean this mess upright now
before we dig ourselves in any deeper.
Now might be our last shot at Guardo.
He's right.
We're all clear.
- Looks like she's Guardo's cooch.
- What are we gonna do with her?
I don't have too much concern
for Guardo's loved ones.
all right. Someone's here.
Don't get trigger happy.
I want this guy alive long
enough to ask him questions.
Hola.it's nydia.
Esta Guardo?
He's not there.
Gracias.
What's she doing now?
She's making lunch.
How's the newfoot patrol going?
It's ok, but community
relations is boring.
We're not getting any action.
Putting a friendly face on
the department is important.
People need to feel comfortable
bringing their problems to us.
Robbery/homicide faxed this over.
It's a composite of the man seen leaving
the side of the san marcos house murders.
Get copies made.Pass it along.
If you're here to get an update on Vic,
I'm too busy. I'll try to find
someone to get you up to speed.
Well, I might have to wait awhile. Your
cupboard down there looks pretty bare.
Half my men are out looking
for Vic. The other half
are helping rhd with
this house slaughter.
Would it make your life any easier if
i could get you additional personnel?
Cops, I need. A future
bill in my mailbox, I don't.
You've been captain for a week.
Your homicide rate's quadrupled.
- What are you talking about?
- The san marcos triangle's a no man's land between
wilshire, central, and farmington.
The body count should've been
divided out in equal percentages.
Their captains managed
to dump all 12 on you.
- How'd they do that?
- You're low on the totem pole.
Just happened.
Crime stats will go down.
All I need is time to make my input.
Actually, things are
only gonna get tougher.
The mexican police authority
is consolidating three prisons.
So any inmates with 3 years or less left
on their sentences are being released.
Based on their gang affiliations, you can
expect a large influx across the border
and up in farmington.
Some are probably already here.
Ok. How does this work?
I file the paperwork for a budget bump.
As far as the wilshire and central
captains, I'll try to persuade them to
even out the percentages so that our
district doesn't take the entire hit.
- It's that easy.
- No.
But that's how it is.
Now, uh, what can you
tell me about Mackey?
Jesus, how long does
it take to eat a salad?
We should be glad she
didn't take a dump.
All right. She's gone.
International prefix.
Guardo's in mexico.Goddammit.
- We're just gonna have to wait then.
- Not necessarily.
- We can't rush this.
- We gotta handle it right.
There's an apb out for
me. This doesn't wait.
Look, neither one of
you can be seen with me.
That means I gotta do this on my own.
Why don't you go back to the
barn. Be my eyes and ears.
Gather as much intel as you can.
You lied to me, aldo. You told me
you didn't know where Guardo was.
You keep coming around here asking questions.
The salvadorans are going to sniff it out.
- You want me killed?
- You lie to me again, I'll do it for them.
- Guardo's in san miguel.
- Why?
- Last favor I have todo for you.
- Fine.
He's bringing a load
of scrips out next week.
Mexi gangs are making a
big play into the game.
- How long has he been in mexico?
- As far as I know,just a couple of days.
Where's your cell phone?
Now leave the keys and
get out. Now get out.
I'll return it with a full tank.
Where have you two been?
Running down that lead for
robbery/homicide. What's going on?
We've been callingyour phones all
morning. Why didn't you pick up?
We turned them off. We were in the
field. We didn't want toblow our cover.
The only reason we're here is
we heard the apb out on Vic.
- You got a search warrant for his house?
- I can't discussthe details.
When was the last time you saw Vic?
Called this morning.Said he
was taking a personal day.
Wagenbach and I need
to speak with you two.
Yeah. Yeah, let's get this cleared up.
Your official statement
taken the night lemansky died
says neither you,Vic, or gardocki
had ever been to the portillo auto body.
- Yeah.That sounds right.
- So why did Vic have a map
of the portillo auto body at his house?
Emolia told us that Vic
was gonna give her $500
to deliver lem to the salvadorans.
We found that exact amount in an
envelope with Vic's prints on it.
You think Vic set lem up?
You're crazier than that ex wife of his.
Emolia made numerous calls
to a salvadoran contact
prior to lemansky's death.
Emolia was outed as a snitch.
She was probably calling
to beg for her life.
That doesn't prove anything.
So how do you explain all
this other evidence here?
I don't know.Maybe, uh,
maybe emolia planted it.
Or you did.
That's gold.
Finish. Go on. I really
want to hear this one.
Well, you investigated Vic for 6 months.
You had every resource the department had
available to you. You came up with nothing.
Now, in the few days after lem dies,
you produce a c.i. willing to testify
against him and the evidence to prove it?
- Come on, man.
- Sounds like you know a lot about telling tall tales.
Planting evidence. Practice
makes perfect,right?
Vic didn't kill lem. He's being set up.
Look, it's no secret things
ended ugly between Vic and emolia.
Maybe this is just bitch's revenge.
So why'd Vic run? Why isn't
he here defending himself,
- answering our questions instead of you?
- He probably doesn't even know you're looking for him.
Dutchboy, come on, man. Are
you really buying this bullshit?
The evidence is right
here.It's right here.
The real question is
what your involvement is.
Vic, it's too late for him.
If you tell uswhere he's hiding,
maybe you can save yourself.
- Como estas.como estas.
- Hermano.
An old amigo of mine
bunkered down in san miguel.
Name's Guardo lima. I need you
to repatriate himto the states.
I'm looking for an amigo,
too. Byz lat soldier.
Rumor is he's in east l.a.
Rocha garrenzi.
Wanted for 3murder for
hires in mexico city.
Got his address,aliases, why
couldn't you bust him down there?
He was protected.
Married a big shotcattle
rancher's daughter.
Rocha got tired of milking the same
heifer. Took off with their two ninos.
I know about some mexican
drugs coming into town.
I might have some leverage.
If rocha's arrested in l.a., the case
could get caught up in international courts.
The mother and rich grandparents
are looking fora quicker solution.
They're willing to pay.I'll cut you in.
- What about rocha?
- I don't carewhat you do with him.
I just need the kids.
I'll meet you back here.
- Oh, yeah.
- What did this Guardo do?
Why do you want him?
He killed my friend.
- Yeah.
- Hey, it's me.
I tried to reach Shane,but
he wouldn't answer.
Well, he's up in interrogation
with kavanaugh and dutch.
- What? What's going on?
- It's not good.
Asher said they found a map of
portillo's auto body in your garbage.
Also a matchbook from the
shop emolia's been working at.
Someone must haveput them there.
They're building a case. You
gotta get back here and fight it.
But they can't prove
anything. I didn't do anything.
It's one thing to have
emolia's statement.
Now they've got corroborating evidence.
Just stay put and keepyour ears open.
Call reyes' gang task force.
You find out which byz lat
is the current king shithead
over in east l.a.
I'll call back in five.
I heard they found evidence on Vic.
Yeah. Maybe a little too much.
What do you mean?
You ever here of occam's razor?
The simplest answer is
usually the right one?
Good. Now apply that
to the lemansky case.
Now all this evidence
is pointing to Vic.
Occam's razor would suggest he's guilty.
Walter chatton's a
contemporary of occam's.
Disputed the razor.
Coined his own anti razor.
- What's that?
- Chatton believed that the world was too complex.
Too many variables to assume that the
simplest answer was always the correct one.
Ok.
What do you think is going on?
The salvadorans had a contract out
on your life yet you never left town.
Why not just high-tail it out of here?
I won't talk to anyone but jon.
Kavanaugh's not here, and
you nee to answer my question.
Only reason I'm in this mess
is because of you assholes.
What's this?
I'm exploring another angle.
I'll catch you up later.
Catch me up. Now.
Ok, we know emolia was greenlit.
What if she was trying to gain
favor with Guardo to save her life?
Cut a deal with him. They kill
lemansky, she pins it on Vic.
Mackey's out there right now, and
you're wasting time talking to her.
- This interrogation,It's over.
- Uh, no. It's not. I'm not finished yet.
We got every cop we
have out looking for Vic.
Look, private tutoring might
buy you favor with your hot unis,
but it doesn't get us any
closer to scooping up Mackey.
If you want to spend your time
exploring pot shot theories
than doing your job like you were
supposed to, we'd have Vic here right now.
And not some innocent
witness. Come on, emolia.
What's up?
I have some concerns about keeping
wagenbach on the lemansky case.
- Why?
- I know he's your guy,
but we may have a perception problem
should this case ever go to trial.
How?
The defense lawyer could argue that
dutch's past relationship with corrine
has strained his objectivity.
Dutch is protecting Vic
for his ex wife's sake?
Their relationship's no secret.
They could argue that he
has a personal stake in this.
What about the personal
nature of the case with you?
I'm still an outsider.
Iad is always going to have
an adversarial relationship
with the people that we investigate.
But the way this caseis breaking,
with the evidence that
we have to back it up,
this could be a big win for you.
Finally getting Mackey off the street.
They're building a
murder case against him.
And it might actually stick.
We can't let him take this hit.
And what if, uh...
What if I said that i
was with lem or something?
You know, had a grenade from the bust.
Just went off by accident.
Making up some bullshit
story is not gonna help.
Plus you'd be admitting
to aiding and abetting.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
We gotta do something for Vic.
The longer he's in the
wind, the guiltier he looks.
- Hey, slow your roll,homes.
- What's your business?
I'm here to see santi.
Charley,nobody sees jefe without
an appointment or a warrant.
I know the local swines, and
i don't recognize your face.
I work farmington.
Same place your shipment of mexican
scrips is headed to next week.
I don't get to break bread with santi,
the scrips are gonna end
up in my evidence locker.
Hay un placade farmington aqul.
Sabe de los valesque vien.
All right. Let's go.
All right.I need your gun.
It's city issue.
- I can't do that.
- Well, then you can'tsee santi.
There. No bullets work for you?
Take a hit. Relax, ese.
No, thanks. I'm good
with the contact high.
So what brings you to the east side?
I need a location on a byz lat
still drying the rio off his back.
Name's rocha.
So let me guess,
i hand him over, and my
scrips make it into town.
Great minds think alike.
- Rocha's valuable to the bosses.
- More valuable than your scrips?
- You don't want to bust that shipment, friend.
- You're not giving me any other choice.
You bust it, you're declaring war.
Not only on the byz lats,
on all the mexi gangs.
I didn't know there was a peace.
I'm gonna give you some
money for your time.
You forget my face. And the scrips.
I don't need your money. I need rocha.
I'm offering you an olive branch.
If you prefer shock and
awe, I can arrange that, too.
Back off,pendejo. Lil'
homie's shitfaced, ese.
Junior missed the short
bus to school today.
Tell him to lower that weapon.
**********************
I ain't afraid of no cops. I'll do it.
You got no bullets,cerdo.
All that smoke make you forget?
I got one in the chamber, dickhead.
Your homeys were too stoned to notice.
One of you shoots me,
my muscle twitch takes
out your bad boy here.
So, either you and I are gonna
leave this basement together,
or we're gonna leave this life together.
You decide.
Stay back.
Back off!
You got to the next red
to tell me where rocha is.
He's putting a hit on a one-niner.
Jumped my lieutenant.
Which one-niner? Which one?
Which one? It's going yellow!
Name's big g.
He deals on eighth and alameda.
By colvin high? When's this going down?
Later today.
Rocha doesn't show up,
or you warn him,
and I'm gonna show up with a hell of
a lot more than one in the chamber.
Now get the hell out!
Well, shit, man. At least slow down,ese.
- Get out!
- Slow down, man!
Big g.
Man, check y'all
niggaz later, all right?
- Yeah, so?
- Your lucky day.
Someone's planning on killing
you, and I actually give a shit.
Well, I guess I best
be going then, right?
You aren't going anywhere.
If the killer can't find
you, then they can't kill you.
And that's gonna be a problem for me.
Hey, what if this vato does a drive-by
and gets some shots off
before y'all get to him?
This guy's a pro.
He's gonna step right up to you, put
two in your chest and one in your head.
Oh, and that's supposed to
make me feel better, right?
Get back to your spot!
Hey. Thanks for coming in.
Two unmarked police sedans have been
parked outside my house all day long.
I was a cop's wife long enough
to know that there's trouble.
When was the last time
you saw or spoke to Vic?
Last night.
He said that someone was trying
to pin lem's murder on him.
A warrant was filed for
his arrest this morning.
For what? For lem's murder?
He would never in a million years.
The evidence is pointing
in that direction.
What evidence?
Oh, my gosh. You don't
believe this, do you?
I mean, there's no way
that he would ever...
Kavanaugh has generated some proof.
Listen, you need to prepare
yourself for this to go either way.
You need to start
preparing the kids. Ok?
- Corrine, wait.
- What are you doing to my husband, huh?
- Your ex husband.
- I know you hate Vic,
but that doesn't give you the
right to destroy my family.
Vic had lemansky killed
because he was a threat.
- The evidence proves it.
- I don't believe you.
I don't believe any of this!
Let's go somewhere else
so we can talk in private.
Get off of me. Where do
you want to go, to my house?
You want to put your hands all over
me again? Lean me up against the door?
Try to screw me to get back at Vic?
In some demented, twisted way?
I only asked you questions.
Yeah, right. You used your
badge to get into my house,
and then you tried to touch me.
I didn't feel safe.
- Um, corrine...
- No, listen to me.
He... He entered my house
under false pretenses.
And then he tried to
sexually assault me.
I want to file charges.
- Are you sure about this?
- Either take my statement,
or I'm gonna file
charges somewhere else.
Just stay there.
Drop it!
All right. Where are
you keeping your kids?
- Who in the hell are you? -
Your father-in-law hired me.
All he wants are the kids. If
you tell me where they're at,
then I'll let you go.
The cavalry's gonna show up any minute.
The moreland motel.
Room 8.
All right. Good.
What about letting me go, man?
Yeah. I feel like shit about that.
- How's corrine?
- She's filing charges.
Sticking to her guns.
Attempted sexual ag.
- You believe her?
- I believe she believes it.
I wouldn't have thought kavanaugh
was capable of something like that.
Makes you wonder what
else he's capable of.
Yesterday, you insinuated
emolia might have been lying.
Setting Vic up. Today, not a peep. Why?
Maybe considering everything
we suspect Vic's done,
you see him going down
for this as some sort of
karmic justice whether he did it or not.
I know he's a bad guy.
The evidence is the evidence.
It's tempting to let sleeping dogs lie.
Especially when the
dog's as rabid as Vic.
But I've got one chance
to right this ship, dutch.
To do it, I have to put an end
to a pattern of silent deals
and moral exchanges that have
steered this place off course.
That means to pursue the truth.
And the truth only.
Yesterday, I thought
emolia was lying to me.
I still do.
I can't prove it, but
I'm starting to think that
kavanaugh is the one
that fed her the lie.
It's one thing believing Vic's innocent,
but to accuse kavanaugh
of setting Vic up,
- that's a whole other can of worms.
- He's already lied to me once.
He said he met emolia
yesterday at sid's coffee.
I pulled footage from the 101
freeway cam. Sid's is clear.
No kavanaugh. No emolia.
The truth may not always
lead us down the path we want.
But it's the only way to fix this place.
Get emolia and bring her back down here.
Mommy, mommy!
mommy!
- You brought their mother?
- She insisted on coming.
Where's Guardo?
- I'm really sorry. I couldn't get to him.
- That's bullshit!
You didn't tell me how connected he is.
I couldn't get close enough to
talk to him let alone shanghal him.
I don't give a shit how connected he is!
I kept my part of the deal.
I expect you to keep yours.
He's got too many people on his payroll.
It's impossible. I'm sorry.
Maybe he's got you on his payroll.
Look, I'll make it up to
you, huh? These people are
paying me well for
delivering these kids.
I'll increase your cut. Plus...
- Ask any other favor.
- I don't want your goddamn money.
I want Guardo!
Look, I'm sorry, but
there's nothing I can do.
Goddamnit!
All right.
Can you get close enough to
him to give him a message?
- I might be able to do that.
- Then you meet me here in 2 hours.
It's nonsense.
I'll call you back.
Uh, captain.
- Why's emolia here?
- I need to ask her some questions.
Great. I'll come with you.
Uh, I prefer some alone time with her.
But you can't question
her without me being there.
The last time I checked, I was
captain of this house not you.
You want to watch, there's a front row
seat for you in the observation room.
It's part of her deal.
She's been burned by
the people here before.
And I promised i
wouldn't leave her alone.
Fine. But you just listen.
Emolia, I'm the one who said those
things about sebastio. It wasn't Vic.
He always took care of
you two, you know that.
Come on. Emolia, please.
Don't do this to him.
Emolia.
I love this room. It's
my favorite one here.
It's kind of ugly.
Cold.
It's not much to look at.
But it brings the truth out in people.
I fixed a lot of wrongs
inside these walls.
That's what we do in here, emolia.
- Find the truth.
- I already told you the truth.
That bullshit story you've been
spinning about Vic? I don't buy it.
That's your problem then.
Guardo wanted to have you killed,
you made up a story about Vic so
that you could get witness protection.
Now does that sound about right?
You can answer her.
It's all right. It's ok.
Vic wanted lem bad.
Gave me his location to
give to Guardo. That's it.
Officer lowe, officer asher, I need you.
I want you out this room.
That's not gonna happen.
- The assistant chief himself...
- I don't care what deal you made.
Either you leave this room on your own,
or I'll have these two
officers do it for you.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
I've read your jacket.
You've been in a lot of trouble,
but nothing like this pissing
match between Vic and kavanaugh.
I'm getting witness
protection. Starting a new life.
- I'm doing ok.
- You're not doing ok.
You're trapped. You're scared.
You're living in fear.
You're ping-ponging
between these two men who
have done nothing but use and abuse you,
and I'd have more
sympathy for you except
you let them do it for a buck.
Emolia: for my son. Your son?
What are you gonna tell your
son about this time of your life?
That you let Vic and
kavanaugh steal away your soul?
Or that you were lost and found
the strength to free yourself?
I know you're scared. I'd be, too.
But I can offer you a
way out if you let me.
- How?
- First you have to tell me the truth.
You've helped this
department out before,
and I can see about
arranging protection.
I'm offering you a way
to be rid of these men forever. Take it.
Because they're leading you down a path
that is destroying you, your son...
and everything around you.
You know it.
Everything is gonna be all right.
You're gonna be ok. I promise.
I need to, uh...
I need to talk to captain wyms.
- I have to talk... please.
- It's ok. It's ok.
But first, you got to tell me the truth.
I fed her the story.
Coerced her statement.
Planted the evidence in Mackey's house.
But I framed a guilty man.
- You guys make sure you weren't tailed?
- Yeah.
- Where's Guardo?
- Tonio boned me.
- Couldn't bag the whale.
- Well, what do we do now?
Switch bait. Nydia home?
Yeah.
Hey, hey, hey. Hey, man.
What's the plan? Just follow my lead.
Nydia Hernandez?
- Yes.
- Detective Mackey.
This is detectives
Vendrell and Gardocki.
What's going on?
We have information that someone's
planning on kidnapping you.
What?
Our department's been investigating
a mexican drug lord named salceda.
An informant of ours
told us that he's...
That he's planning to
kill your boyfriend Guardo.
To take over his drug
protection business.
I don't know any Guardo.
- You're not his girlfriend?
- No.
Never heard of the guy.
Wow.
Then, maybe we're looking
for another Nydia Hernandez.
Well, I'm sorry to disturb you
if you're not his girlfriend,
you got nothing to worry about.
Wait.
Guardo told me never to talk to cops.
Why would someone want to kidnap me?
It's Guardo Salceda wants.
But he's in Mexico.
Kidnapping you,
to use you as bait to
lure Guardo back to L.A.
We were worried we weren't
going to get to you in time.
We need to get you into a safehouse
while we hunt down Salceda.
Well, I should call Guardo. Warn him.
No, we don't know who's
listening on his side of the line.
Our intel says it's an inside job.
We have to move you now.
- How long is thisgonna take?
- A day. Two at the most.
Ronnie will take you to
the safehouse immediately.
We'll pack some clothes for
you. Meet you there, all right?
Come on. We better get going.
Ok.
What the hell are you doing?
Vic?
Just pack. I'll explain later.
I never cheated on anything before.
The first time I do, I get caught...
taking the dirtiest man
i ever met off the street.
You set another cop up for murder.
Threw away your career.
I fail to see the humor.
I guess I didn't have enough practice
planting evidence,
manipulating witnesses,
and covering my tracks. You sacrificed
your integrity for Vic Mackey.
You are betterthan that. You
used to be better than him.
I still am.
Take his gun and badge.
You're under arrestfor interfering in
police business under color of authority.
I assume other charges will follow.
- Put him in the cage?
- No.
Take him straight to police one.
Cuff him in front. Keep it quiet.
At least I have Mackey out of my life.
He's not my problem anymore.
He's yours.
What's this?
It's the message I want
you to deliver to Guardo.
A necklace?
Deliver it to him in person.
You tell him that
Nydia's been kidnapped.
If he ever wants tos ee her again,
he has 24 hours to get
fifty grand in cash,
in person to L.A.
I don't think I want any part of this.
Let alone what you do to
him after you've got him.
- Vic, come on. Think about this.
- You're delivering a message.
Your involvement ends there.
And I'll for go my cut
for the returned kids.
Ok.
You tell Guardo, call Nydia's cell
phone when he wants to set the meet.
Hey, hey. A ransom?
The last thing we need
is more dirty money.
I don't give a shit about the 50 grand.
Once Guardo finds out Nydia's been
kidnapped, he'll have to come to L.A.
Word gets out he can't
protect his own girlfriend,
who's gonna trust him
to protect their drugs?
Vic, don't do this.
Please.
Lem's gone.
Nothing we can do can bring him back.
If you push this too far,
man, we're gonna lose you, too.
Guardo has to pay.
- Where's Nydia?
- The bedroom sleeping.
This just turned into a kidnapping.
- What do you mean?
- Vic sent a messageto Guardo.
If he doesn't meet us
in 24 hours, she dies.
- What do we do if he doesn't show?
- Oh, he'll show.
- This her cell phone?
- Yeah.
If he does show, what do we do with
her? I don't know what I'm gonna do yet.
Vic, this is wrong.
You two don't have to be involved
in this. Go back to the barn.
Keep your distance from me.
Good job.
How's he doing?
- He's beautiful. I'll see you.
- How are you?
I'm exhausted.
He's been colicky.
Keeping me up all night.
Well, I do havesome good news i
wanted to tell youface to face.
Any excuse to get out of the
house. I need some adult time.
You passed the sergeant's exam.
- Congratulations.
- Oh, God.
Bless you.
So I start wearing these as soon
as my maternity leave is over, huh?
The slot's available
effective immediately.
If you don't take it, your name
goes back to the bottom of the list.
You mean I have to come
back to work right away?
Or you pick another slot if it opens up.
That's what happens when men make the rules.
You sleep on it, let me know in the morning.
Hey, either of you two
seen or heard from Vic?
If you do, tell him he can go home.
Why is that?
Because the case against
him has been dropped.
So, if he is still in the country,
tell him he can sleep
in his own bed tonight.
You're clear.
You can go back to work.
Just let Nydia go.
We got a reprieve.
- Dutchboy and Claudette saved our asses.
- Let's just wake her up and get her out of here, man.
She's how we're going to get to Guardo.
What happened to no more
unilateral decisions.
Shane's right.
I want this guy just as bad as you,
- but not like this. This is too risky.
- Every second,
he gets to breathe,
and Lem doesn't is unacceptable.
I'll do it myself.
What is your problem?
Can you listen to anybody but yourself?
Lem wouldn't listen about going to Mexico. He's
dead because of it. Is that what you want, man, huh?
You want to die? You want to go
to jail? You want us to go to jail?
Huh?
Go home. Get some shut eye.
I'll guard the fort for the night.
I'll just be a minute.
You've been a very busy boy.
Planting evidence. Coercing witnesses.
Assaulting my ex wife.
I learned from the master.
I told you you weren't
ready to play at this level.
Wouldn't have mattered even if I was.
The truth is,
isn't your time yet.
But it'll happen.
The universe will take out
its trash when it's ready.
Looks like it already has.
You corrupted everything around you.
Turned a good man like Lemansky
into a thug and a thief.
And you got him killed for it.
I tried to become you
for a minute. But...
it wasn't worth it.
I'll take my lumps. Go back to my life.
But I won't be the one hearing my
dead friend's screams in my head.
You preach all the
existential bullshit you want.
But I'm the one going home to
my bed while you're still here.
I'm at peace.
Are you?
Soon enough.