Previously on The Shield...
Got 12 dead mexicans slaughtered
in their house in San Marcos.
But no arrests.
I'll make some calls.
A name keeps popping up
in my interviews. Hernan.
Hernan is undercover in
the salvadoran organization.
Stop trying to contact him.
Hey, Moses!
I thought we told you
to stay away from between her pussy.
You're gonna stop seeing that asshole.
I know.
So this guy targets runaways.
While telling them to go home.
There's another girl.
Came in 6 months ago.
We didn't believe her.
Congratulations on getting
another girl ass raped.
Anything you can tell us...
Where he held you?
It was a girl's room.
Posters on the wall
were all white boys
in these gay poses.
This Kevin Hiatt is ours
starting next week.
You're not adding
anybody to my team
that I don't have approval of.
He's not your addition.
He's your replacement.
Hiatt's decided to add another
member to the Strike Team.
I suggested you.
All right.
Shane?
Lem, I'm sorry!
But I had to, right?
We're gonna find out who did this.
And we're gonna kill him.
It's Guardo.
He stepped on his
protection plate twice.
You know, maybe he didn't do it, man!
If it wasn't Guardo, who was it?!
Well, let's get him, man!
Found him swirling in a gutter.
Conscious?
In and out.
Contusions, possible fractures.
Vitals are stable.
Put him in curtain two.
All right.
Call the resident to check
for internal bleeding.
Better tell him to hurry.
Thought you said he was stable.
He is, but we found this.
He's a cop.
Shane?
Corrine, what the hell happened?
He was beaten pretty badly
and doesn't remember how.
Where? When?
They found him a few blocks from here.
Oh, man.
No shit from you guys.
Already took
one pounding today.
What happened?
I was walking to my truck,
next thing I know
I'm coming to in a meat wagon.
You didn't see anyone?
Left my wallet.
Badge, gun.
Think it might've been the salvadorans?
Some lame ass attempt at one of us?
Payback for Guardo?
We wouldn't be having
this conversation.
This was just a good
old-fashioned shit-kicking.
It was probably some asshole
we sent up, fresh out.
I'll run down recent releases,
check in with the P.O.'s.
Tell me something first...
Who's this guy?
New girlfriend likes baby
smooth skin between her thighs.
You should have her call me.
Oh, my god.
What happened?
What the doctors say?
The X-rays are all good.
I'll get working on who did this.
Baby, what happened to you?
Transcript : Swsub.com
Synchro : Artusamak
Haunts
How's Shane doing?
Hurting for certain.
Not especially pleasing
to the eye at the moment.
I'm going to post a protective detail
outside his room until we know more.
What do you know about
the San Marcos house murders?
I heard about them.
Grisly stuff.
Yeah.
Robbery homicide's running with it.
We got the hand-off.
Aceveda's all over this.
10 days ago my detective
found 12 bodies, hacked to pieces.
Well, 11 bodies, one arm.
Machete's the weapon of
choice for the salvadorans.
Which supports the tip that
Aceveda's cronies gave us,
that the killers were el salvadorians,
the victims were all mexican illegals.
3 women, 9 men.
I.d.'s?
All but the arm.
Mexican government had
them in their system.
If you can call that a system.
The men were all from the same prison.
Released 2 days before
the bodies were found.
It's all in the there.
This becomes
the Strike Team's top priority now.
Solving it quickly
is the difference
between keeping the barn
open or closing it for good.
They're shutting
this place down?
Not if you put a dozen murders
in the win column.
Make our closure rate
too good-looking to lose us.
Get with Dutch.
He found the bodies.
Uh, the barn going out of
business stays between us.
Last thing Farmington needs
is cops who feel like lame ducks.
Alright. Let's have a look at it.
Give me a sec?
So far, no one on the street's bragging
about giving Shane a beat down.
All right. Well, have the units
keep their eyes and ears open.
What, man?
Guardo's girlfriend...
She could've figured out we used her
to get him, told his people...
Maybe the salvadorans are after us.
I don't think so, man.
Shane got hit with a fist,
not a machete or a grenade.
Let's go.
RHD's pretty thorough.
They give us a starting
place with the victims?
Like she said.
Released from a prison in Sinaloa.
Connections to the same mexican cartel.
All with guest worker visas.
Let me see that.
Prisoners don't get work visas.
Especially not real ones.
A- plus forgeries then.
Where do you want me to start, jefe?
It's either give you a hand
or be out on the street, right?
I've still got some drag at I.N.S.
so I'll get them to run
a quick I.D. on the arm.
But you know these streets
better than anyone.
Where do you want to start?
With the visas.
You know anyone that does
that quality of work?
I might know a guy.
By the way, welcome to the team.
Won't let you down.
He's the boss now.
Don't let him down.
Let's go.
Graciela sanchez is getting
out of mission cross today.
How are we doing iding her rapist?
Billings is pounding the pavement
with the sketch Princess gave us.
The feds are running
the profile I came up with
through their database
for potential unsubs.
Contact the local y's, teen shelters...
I did it, I did it. No one's
gotten back to me yet.
Stay on top of them.
Our guy's M.O.'s escalating.
Wouldn't surprise me
if he's already got a fresh victim.
Oh, my god.
What are you doing?
Details of the crime scene,
create a written report
for the files on this case.
Who wants what and why
and how slaughtering
all those people in this room
helped achieve that goal.
That's all you need
to be writing down, man.
Hey, hey.
I don't want to be here.
Too bad.
12 people.
3 of them women.
Cut to pieces in this place 10 days ago.
I read about it in the paper.
I didn't need to see it.
They were carrying these.
Only one guy I know
good enough to produce
this kind of work and that's you.
I changed careers.
If not you, then who?
I couldn't say.
Paper men, we have a code.
You got a code.
You the blood on these walls? Huh?
You see it?
You have no idea the pressure to point
the finger at someone for this.
No matter how bogus that I.D.
Look again.
I-I can tell you these
were done in mexico, not here.
Hiatt: How can you be so sure?
The font. T-they use an older version.
It's almost the same, but not quite.
Mexicans and the sals, troubled times.
Latinos can't even trust
each other these days.
Wait outside.
Brown and Brown, it's a place to start.
Body count like this,
the aztecs and mayans
are squabbling over more
than who invented the burrito.
So let's start with the salvadorans.
Thank you, sheriff.
Didn't expect to see
your grenade tossing ass
for at least another 30 years.
Tejado: Oh, it's your lucky day.
Oh, Guardo's number 2 has arrived.
Why are your old amigos
beefing with the mexicans?
Day trip for me,
but you wasted your time.
Get your feet down!
I'm just enjoying the air.
What's it gonna take
to make it worth my time?
Look, I want to know if Guardo
or any other salvadorans
were behind the San Marcos murders.
You get one request.
I deny it, that's it,
you're back in your hole.
But if it's something reasonable...
I want my dick sucked by a hottie.
Right here on the table.
Thought it was gonna
be something difficult.
Alright. Info first, dick suckin' next.
OK. They killed Guardo.
The mexicans.
When?
He came back to LA a week ago.
Bam bam.
Just disappeared.
Explains why we can't find him.
Guardo works for the cartel.
Why the bad blood?
Yo no se.
Hey, that dick ain't gonna suck itself.
That's the straight-up truth.
Beaners the ones started this beef.
Salvas gonna finish it.
So, Guardo's MIA, presumably dead,
you're wearing orange.
Who's gonna take up the fight?
It's been worked out
in upper management.
Octavio...
Rodrigo...
Hernan...
I know the first two. Who's this hernan?
New guy. Wants to be the shot caller.
If he's such a player,
how come he's a mystery man to me?
Just here from Salvador.
Yeah?
Where?
Hey! What about my hummer?
Asher.
Come here.
You're considered a hottie
in certain circles, right?
Damn straight. Why?
This is Tejado.
He's got a special request for you.
Yeah?
What's that?
Yeah, that was Moses.
The one-niner ball?
Yeah, he's got some intel on Shane.
I know this is
the first priority, though.
Wyms wants you on a short leash.
So don't go walking into traffic,
make me look bad.
Your friend Graciela's been
released from the hospital.
You know she was raped.
Who's Graciela?
According to the girls at
the Rec Center, you 2 are pretty tight.
How long you been on the street?
By law we're required to
send runaways back home.
But if you cooperate, tell us
everything you know about Graciela...
And promise to go back home on your own,
We'll take you at your word.
I haven't seen her lately.
Any strange men ever
followed her around?
Acting suspicious toward her?
There's this one guy at
Ray's who was creeping us out.
The burger stand on Wilcox?
J.B.
We'd smile, he'd give us
free burgers and shit.
Ever feel sick after J.B. feeds you?
No. Why?
According to the girls
you were quite friendly.
Giving them free food.
They're lying. I never did that.
'cause if you stole from your employer,
that's a parole violation.
You homesick for the joint, J.B.?
Look, maybe I talked
to them once or twice.
Gave 'em leftovers. So?
Talking to them's one thing.
Spiking their soda with GHB,
sodomizing and
torturing them's another.
I didn't do that shit.
It's gotta be tough to
meet a nice girl your age.
Ex-con,
pulling minimum wage.
But a homeless,
hungry 15-year-old runaway,
Easy to impress with a burger and fries.
Hey, hey,
it's cool, it's cool.
You better pray you
didn't hurt that foot
sticking it up a white cop's ass.
Easy, dude.
I'm rocking a pimp stick
'cause I'm cold like that.
You got something to say about Shane?
Start talking.
You remember Tilli?
That chick I was with
the last time we met.
What, that 12-year-old you're sticking?
She's 18 and old enough for your boy
to be tapping that ass behind my back.
You expect us to believe
Shane is banging that chick?
That's what I said.
Only reason I brought
y'all down is because
y'all gonna have reason
to think I beat him down.
Riding up in your girl's steeze
works as motive for me.
I ain't hit that shit in a minute.
And I ain't about no sloppy seconds.
Word, I did not take flight on your boy.
Not that I would a minded.
Then who did?
Ask the l'il ho.
Seem like she all about telling
the white man what he wanna hear.
Hey, I'm Detective Wagenbach.
Carlos Morganza.
Children's beacon.
The runaway shelter on Western.
You sent out an alert to us?
Thanks for coming in.
You're actually the first
person to get back to me.
Well, when I heard
what happened to those girls,
I put together a list of the kids
I thought were most at risk.
You know, drugs, prostitution.
Is there any way we can confirm
which of these kids have been seen
and which haven't
in the last 24 hours?
I'll do what I can.
Thanks for coming in.
Oh, um, my daughter
sabrina went missing.
It's been 3 years now.
Her case got cold,
the police had other priorities.
If you could take a look.
When I get a chance, absolutely.
- Thank you.
Just take it easy.
A little slower.
Hey.
Sorry.
Jesus. We're gonna find out
who did this.
How ya doing?
You just saw the only part
of him that's not bruised.
The Captain sent me over
here to take a statement.
I already told Vic
everything that happened.
Yeah. Well, I also have
orders to park myself
out here as your protective detail.
I'll be fine. I was just in
the wrong place at the wrong time.
I got orders.
I'll be right outside.
Thanks.
You got it? OK.
Feds faxed over some suspects
that fit your profile.
Anything turn up at J.B.'s place?
No signs he placed prison runaways.
It's a fourth floor walk-up.
He'd have to take his victims
up 4 flights of stairs.
Paper thin walls.
Hard to believe he could do
that without somebody noticing.
Good luck.
Detective Wagenbach.
Carlos. Detective Billings,
Carlos Morganza.
He's a counselor
at the children's beacon.
I got involved about 3 years ago
when my own daughter went missing.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Listen, my colleagues and I checked
into that list of high-risk
kids like you asked.
These are the names of the ones
we've lost touch with most recently.
This is great. Thank you.
Sure. Listen, I can run
through them with you.
You know what?
I'm in the weeds right now,
but if you can sit at my desk,
I can get a uni to take notes.
Oh. Sure.
Thank you.
Dutchman.
Remind me again your
profile of our bad guy.
Why, so you can shit all over it?
No, I'm serious.
Uh, he's a single father,
whose daughter disappeared
or died prematurely.
What kind a douche bag breaks his ass
for no reason trying to help the cops?
He's got a missing...
Right? A lot of these freaks
like to insert themselves
into investigations.
Uh, you know what, Carlos,
I think I can make time
for you right now.
Claudette Wyms.
This is Cruz Pezula.
I wanted to introduce Cruz
to the new Captain.
More like the fresh meat
in Farmington. Hello.
It's a pleasure.
What's the latest on
the San Marcos massacre?
I'm sorry.
Are you with the police
committee as well?
No, I'm not.
I can vouch for Cruz.
He's well respected in the community.
In fact, he's the one who
passed on that information
about the possible
salvadoran connection.
I know a lot of people
who are devastated
by this new level of violence.
As are we all.
Claudette has
the committee's full support.
How many Detectives you got on it?
It's the entire Strike Team.
Mackey, too?
Kevin Hiatt's taking point.
He was with INS 4 years.
The victims are all mexican nationals...
He's more than qualified.
I should hope so.
Could you give us a minute?
Of course.
Don't ever ambush me like that again.
He has concerns. I share them.
I don't care how plugged in to
your constituency that guy is.
Bringing a civilian into
a confidential police matter
undermines the investigation
and my authority.
I meant no disrespect.
But perhaps you wouldn't be taking it
so personally if you had
more facts to share.
I'm sorry, Captain.
I didn't know you were in here.
Would it be OK if we used this room
to talk to Mr. Morganza?
No. I'm in the middle of something
with the councilman.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Would it be all right if
we talked in interrogation?
It's a little less personal. Sorry.
- Sure. Yeah. No problem.
- OK.
Hey, Tilli!
Get over here!
Yo, why you calling me out
in front of my peoples?
I'm a cop.
I hear you like cops.
That some sort of code or something?
I know about you and Shane.
He's in the hospital.
- What for?
- Somebody jumped him.
I figured you could tell us who.
Wait. He caught a smackdown?
Is he a'ight?
I want to go see him.
Which hospital?
His wife's with him right now.
I'll say I'm a friend.
Shane doesn't have
too many teenage black friends.
How'd you get this?
My stepdad.
Your stepdad know you're
spreading your legs for Shane?
He got pretty angry.
I told him it wasn't his business.
And if he tried to stop it,
or put his hands on me again,
Shane would kick his ass.
Where's he at now?
Hell if I know.
Where's he work?
He don't.
He about that monthly
check from the county.
Look, if he did that to Shane,
what do you think he's gonna do
to me the next time I see him?
You stay away from the hospital
and stay away from your old man.
I'll take care of him.
Corrine, that percocet's not working.
I'll ask the resident
for something stronger.
Thanks.
Listen, before I forget,
these are his personal items,
including his car keys...
One of the unis removed
the bullets from his gun.
Those things scare the hell out of me.
Thanks.
Can you give us a minute, please?
Sure.
Thanks.
God damn you!
How could you?
Shit! Jesus! What?
Why do you need condoms
when I'm 3 months pregnant?
They must have been from before.
Mara, I'm not doing anything, baby.
I swear.
Son of a bitch.
Yes, you are!
Does it have anything to do
with the reason why you're here?
Does it?
Oh, no.
Mara, it's nothing.
It's nothing.
It's not important.
Look, I'm...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I've just... I've been all twisted up.
I'm, I'm. You?
This is us, OK? Our family.
You threw it away.
And for what?
I've been trying to help
you through all of this,
you waking up screaming,
and then you're out...
Oh, I can't believe you!
Jesus!
This is for the pain.
When sabrina first went missing,
everyone pitched in to help find her.
Friends, neighbors, my church.
But after a while, people go
back to their routines.
Life goes on.
Even the police move on
to other business.
But she's still out there.
We appreciate you helping.
All I can say is, as a parent myself,
it's gotta be awful.
Your heart breaks all over again
every day you don't hear from her.
There are 15 kids on your list.
Is there any one you feel
is a particular risk to this predator?
Oh, probably...
Rosanna.
She had a pimp. Had his claws in her.
Once that happens,
it sets up a whole victim mentality
and that's an open invitation.
When was the last time anyone saw her?
2, 3 weeks ago.
Dutch?
Kevin Hiatt.
New here.
Yeah, I know. Welcome.
Thanks. Hey, listen.
We're running with
the San Marcos house murders.
I was just wondering if you
had any files I should see?
Uh, yeah. Give me a few minutes,
I'll get them together.
Sure. Cool. Hey, listen.
What do you know about
a guy named Hernan?
Um... Come here.
He's a Fed'.
He's undercover in the
salvadoran organization.
So, how do I get in touch with him?
You don't.
I tried.
Female fed showed up
on my door at midnight
saying she's Hernan's handler
and to back the hell off.
What agency?
I.C.E.
So don't waste your time.
Well, it's my time to waste, right?
What's his handler's name?
Vic Mackey!
Jesus Christ.
The ghost of christmas past!
You're looking good, man.
For an old guy.
I see them baldness cures
still ain't for shit.
Oh, watch it.
Hey, I heard about your guy.
Curtis was a good kid.
Well, none of us get outta this
place in one piece, right?
Yeah. I was away for the funeral.
Is there some sort of a charity
or police memorial fund or something?
Audubon society.
Lem was really into birds, turns out.
OK.
Things really turned
around for you, looks like.
Yeah. You know, I got
my feet underneath me.
Doing pretty good. It took a minute,
but I'm doing pretty good.
Look, I got a business
proposition for you.
Look, rain check, man.
I got 12 D.B.'s, no suspect.
My partner took a beating.
Not only am I flying solo,
I gotta locate who did it
and return the favor.
Come on, Vic. You helped me
through a rough patch, man.
I'm just trying to, you know,
pay back the kindness.
Come on, come on.
Take a ride with me.
I'll have you back in 30.
You're living large,
driving around in a high-end
pussy magnet like this.
Only now I got a 26-year-old filipina
I gotta keep in Gucci.
The buzz is you're getting squeezed out.
Maybe without a pension.
I'm not getting squeezed out.
And nobody's got their hand
in my pocket either.
What's the job?
Citizen, east LA., he owns
an apartment building.
Wants to spruce it up
and raise the rents.
Only there's this undesirable
element camped out there.
So the landlord wants
to hire a cleaning crew.
Jamaican dope operation's got the run
of the place, terrorizing Lieutenants.
Can't evict 'em, long
as the rent's on time.
Need a little hand persuading
them to move elsewhere, man.
My plate's pretty full right now.
Vic, there's families
living in this place.
There's little kids riding their bikes
next to these dope deals going down.
The landlord's paying
good money, too, right?
Cash. All right? Half up front.
Look, man, just scope it out.
If it looks good to you,
having a real badge around'll
make this thing go a lot smoother.
Besides, I can't do it without you.
Let's look.
Yeah. Come on! Come on!
Spotter.
Embedded with innocents.
Glad I was wrong about
your getting shoved out.
It's a shitty way to go.
Everybody knows you got a raw deal.
It was goddamned embarrassing.
I mean, you shit blood for 'em,
then you don't get to
leave on your own terms.
Hope you never have
to go through that.
Yeah.
There's security.
Yeah, and probably 2 more upstairs.
Cashier guy, one at the door.
I'm gonna take a pass on this, Joe,
and whether you realize it or
not, you should do the same.
You don't understand.
Vic, this is my only
paycheck this month.
I really gotta get going back.
Can you at least run
priors on this place,
let me see what level asswipe
I'm dealing with here?
Yeah, sure.
It's Rosanna.
She had a pimp. Had his claws in her.
Once that happens, it sets
up a whole victim mentality,
and that's
an open invitation.
Is that him, baby?
I'm sure that's his voice.
You're positive?
I was pretty out of it,
but if there's a voice
I'll never forget, it's his.
Entrance off the alley.
Yeah, he pulls up,
takes the victims inside
without anyone seeing.
Yep.
Hope your profile didn't say
anything about him being a neat freak.
You wouldn't want a
cleaning lady coming around
if you were holding
a girl prisoner.
Dutch.
Rosanna?
Sabrina's room.
Concert poster Princess rembered.
What 15-year-old keeps
her room this neat?
The mess in the rest of
the house, he's letting go,
falling apart, in here,
he's preserving her memory,
or an idealized version of it anyway.
God, and what a clean-up job.
Shampoo, wax.
I wouldn't count on any hair fibers.
Yeah.
We talked to Tilli.
Her old man got the drop on me.
It's nothing.
It's just a thing...
- Jesus Christ, Shane.
- Like no one in this car's
ever had a little outta
bounds ass before.
This is an 18-year-old girl,
who's bedded down with
the head of the one-niners.
She's done with him.
Ask her.
You saying this is about
more than getting laid?
Look, everything's cool.
She just shot off
her mouth about us
to the dickhead stepdad
and I got blindsided.
Yeah, I can see that.
Might wanna raise the
mistress bar a little bit.
If you still want a wife
and kid to come home to.
You ever think
about just coming clean?
About everything?
No.
Yeah, I know.
I guess we just have to live with it.
All right.
It's dealer's choice on the stepdad.
Either Ronnie and I can
take care of him tonight,
or wait until you're
strong enough to join in.
No.
No, just let it go.
This guy knowingly laid hands on a cop.
This isn't just about your bruised ego.
There's a principle.
Look, I don't want you
to do anything, please?
I got enough to deal with.
Mara?
Mara.
Mara, come on.
Look, this is stupid.
Mara, please,
just open the door.
Some black bitch called on your phone.
She wanted to know if you were OK.
She sounded like she was 10.
Is that who you're banging
while I got morning sickness?
- Mara.
- Just...
You've always been an asshole.
Mara, please, I just...
Yeah, I know, you're
all torn up over Lem.
Get out.
I don't want our son or the new one
growing up anywhere near you.
Get out!
OK.
What's up?
My guy at INS I.D.'d the arm
from the San Marcos house.
Eduardo Romero.
That supposed to mean something?
Romero's a mid-level bureaucrat
in the mexican government.
Presidential appointment.
Traveling around with a bunch
of drug-connected convicts?
One of their own officials.
This guy should have
been the first one
the mexican government would've I.D.'d.
So why didn't they tell us?
Could embarrass a lot of powerful people
on both sides of the border.
That's right.
Huh.
Stop! No notes.
This doesn't exist for
anybody but us right now.
The captain asked for an update.
You heard what I said.
- What am I supposed to do...
- Hey, no report.
This is raw intel.
We don't even know where it leads yet.
The difference between
the units and the Strike Team
is you don't hand your
superior pieces of a puzzle,
you hand them the whole picture.
Sorry to keep you waiting so long.
We talked to local pimps,
put unis out on the street
trolling the places where
you said Rosanna works.
In the meantime, are there any other
places you can think of we should look?
Not really.
Think hard.
Sometimes we can locate kids
just from personal
information about them.
Kinda movies they like, where they eat,
music they listen to.
Yeah. I mean, you
show me a kid's room,
and I can tell you their life story.
You searched my house, didn't you?
Why would we do that?
You looked in my daughter's room.
You won't find anything there.
We've got two witnesses
that can I.D. you as the rapist.
They recognize your voice
and they rember the poster
in your daughter's room.
My lawyer'll have me out of here
before your shift ends.
I'll be home before you guys.
You want to find your daughter, right?
Right?
You tell us what we want to know,
I will personally re-open her case
and do everything I can to find her.
You want answers?
All right. I'll give 'em to you
but only in front of a news reporter.
I want Sabrina's story aired on tv.
I won't let you all bury her away again.
Couple 211's, possession.
One of 'em caught an "F" for ag assault.
Mostly minor stuff.
If you round up a few more guys...
I'm sorry to leave you hanging.
Oh, no worries.
My buddy's waiting outside.
We can handle this.
Lotta ghosts in this place, man.
Every day is Halloween.
I'll walk you out.
Goddamn freeway.
This city's turning into
a third world shitbag.
This is Lester. Vic Mackey.
Know you by reputation.
I haven't been south of
pico or east of the 110
since I turned the badge in.
Yeah. Well, this'll be good
exercise for you then, huh?
Maybe you should take a couple
more bodies with you on this one, Joe.
Afro-humps'll be so stoned
they won't even know what hit them.
These guys seem like
they're on their game.
One of them caught
a weapons charge recently.
Trust me. Raids like this,
I used to do in my sleep.
Literally.
Hey, Joe.
Yeah?
You still need a wingman?
I'll have you back here in a hour.
So, what's your shot
in all this?
Punishing these girls for running away,
get back at your own kid
for disappearing?
If it gets one girl to go home,
back to her parents...
That's a gift I was never given.
These girls were only anally penetrated.
This wasn't about pleasure.
It was punishment.
Thing I'm having trouble understanding
is how putting these girls through hell
was going to get your daughter back?
Well, you people gave up
looking for her, didn't you?
3 measly goddamn months
of investigating you just gave up.
Look, I'm responsible, too.
I could've made it easier for her.
But without her mother...
Wait. Why did she leave?
Look, I've told you my story.
Find her. She's been
missing for 3 years.
You know what, I may have to rework
the rapist's profile, Steve,
because our suspect
is beginning to look like a person
of interest in a murder investigation.
I didn't kill Sabrina!
My own daughter?
Look, she's alive.
I just can't find her myself.
You're still not telling
us the whole truth.
The deal's off unless you come
a hundred percent clean.
You didn't kill her?
Why'd she leave?
Give me the videotape and get out.
Give me the video.
No, no. OK, OK.
No, I'll tell you.
Just make her turn
the camera off first.
Turn it off.
Sabrina's mother died when she was 9.
Hodgkin's disease.
Sabrina never got over it.
I mean...
Neither of us did.
She began to look...
More and more like Carly.
When I'd...
When I'd hold her in my arms
in bed at night, it was...
Almost like my wife was still with me.
I don't think Sabrina understood just
how much like her she was.
In every way.
You molested your daughter?
Turn the camera back on, please.
Sabrina, honey, if you hear this...
I never meant to hurt you.
Oh, Jesus.
I never meant to be so selfish.
Come back home.
Please.
Lester: How long does it take to cop?
Spook gives the money,
spook gets the dope.
Been in there for 20 minutes.
With brothers, goddamn handshakes
can burn up 10 minutes easy.
Garlic?
Makes you stink.
Gives you an intimidating
psychological advantage.
No, I'll pass.
I'd like to get laid tonight.
I heard that.
Let's do this.
Let's go!
Clear!
Hey!
Hey, ho!
Get away from that damned door!
Get away from it! Down on your knees!
Come on!
Move, man!
Hey, watch it!
Son of a bitch!
Fore!
Clear now.
With a sheepdog, huh?
That's how she made you?
Just read me...
Come on, man.
Easy, man.
The locks, man!
You ain't no real cops!
Shut up!
How much you want?
We'll cut you
devils in for half.
Gimme the super glue.
Get his hands.
Come on!
You dumb...
All righty.
Get up. Go on.
This is some felonious bullshit, man!
Shut up.
Assholes who don't
listen don't get to speak.
Hey, hey, hey!
That's enough.
Man: What do you want, man?
Money? Ganja?
Come on, bitch!
Take it, take it.
Take it! Jesus!
Come on. Get in there!
Come on!
Piss or bleed. Your choice.
Oh, boy.
That's it, baby.
Yeah.
That's good!
Now...
Like a good fella, take a drink
out of the toilet and lap it up.
- Lap it up.
- No, man. I ain't getting...
Man, come on, drink! Drink!
Lap it up, boy!
Lap it! Yeah!
That's it!
Jesus Christ!
This is your official eviction notice.
As of right now, you are
no longer tenants of this building.
You hear me?
Yeah, man.
Landlord's got another apartment
building in south central.
I'm done.
I'll get rid of Lester.
I'll help you with that.
Guess all that bad ass noise
I heard about you's bullshit.
Guess so. Look, you guys
are going the other way.
I'll call a black and white for a ride.
Come on, Vic. Get in, get in.
Let him go, man.
We don't need him.
Word is most of the guys
on his team end up dead anyhow.
Vic.
Vic!
Detective! Did Sabrina make the news?
Yeah, it was the lead story.
Oh, good.
Oh, that's good.
After the segment ran,
another division got an anonymous tip.
Said they'd find her body
out in a grave near lake Elsinore.
Police there just dug up a body.
No. No, that's
somebody else's little girl.
It's not... That's just some
kind of a prank, is what that is!
Some asshole saw the story
and just wanted to hurt me!
No. My Sabrina just needs to hear me.
Ask her to come home.
Your daughter's dead!
You made her run away!
She got killed!
That's Hernan in the blue shirt.
I sweet-talked the I.C.E.
queen into letting us
have some face time with the boy,
so long as I promised we'll be subtle.
Gonna have to treat him
like any other bad guy.
Ready?
- Yeah.
- Here we go.
Hey, stop, stop fighting!
We know who you are.
You're Hernan.
Agent Zinman told me where to find you.
Who are you?
We're on the same side.
Get up. Come on.
Make it look great for the boys.
We heard about some trouble
with the salvadorans and the mexicans.
Tell me you assholes didn't risk
blowing my cover for that.
What we got is the salvadorans
might have called for a hit
on the San Marcos house,
then the mexicans retaliated
by killing Guardo Lima.
It wasn't the salvis.
Word is it was some other mexicans.
Killed their own?
Unlikely.
Especially when one of the victims
was a government official.
Eduardo Romero. You know him?
No. It's probably some internal beef.
Look, my guess...
Guardo's collateral damage.
Well, it serves him right.
Prick blew up a friend of mine.
What, that cop?
Guardo didn't do that.
I don't care what side
this guy's on, he's full of shit.
We all knew Emolia
was snitching to I.A.D.
We knew she was up in
the safe house on Harvest.
We know she's up in Seattle
right now at her sister's.
But the word came down, no distractions.
These guys don't take out their own rat,
no way they'd kill a cop.
It was somebody else.
Shit, Guardo wasn't even up here then.
He was in Mexico with me.
Is anyone gonna make this look good?
Come on, come on!
Get up for me!
Guardo didn't kill Lem.
Maybe he's wrong...
He's not wrong!
He's not wrong.
Gimme your hand.
Get out.
Baby, please...
Just go.
Please, just ask me to come back.
No.
Baby, please, I'm begging you, please.
Just ask me to come back
right now. Please.
Our son is in the other room.
OK. You've got to forgive me.
Look, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
What I did was wrong.
I know it. Please, Mara, please.
God. Please, just take me back.
You want me to forgive you
for sleeping with a girl
that is barely out
of an inner-city middle school?
Forget it. Go ahead. Shoot me.
Shoot yourself. I'm not forgiving you.
Jackson can never know what I've done.
Our son can never know what we've done.
Did Vic get you involved in something?
He doesn't even know.
I killed Lem.
I did.
I did it.
I dropped the grenade in his lap
and I just walked away.
And he was...
He was still breathing, he was alive,
and I just...
I just left him there, you know.
I just... No.
Mara, I-I killed him.
Why?
For us.
Mara, I did it for us.
I thought he was gonna take a deal.
That he was gonna give us all away.
I thought he was gonna
take me away from you,
from Jackson, from our baby.
I didn't know what else to do, Mara.
Now it's all wrong.
It's all wrong.
It just keeps going all wrong.
God, please, God, please,
please forgive me, please!
I can't... I can't do this any more.
I'm sorry.
Please, just ask me back.