Previously on The Shield...
He's got a gun!
Grenades.
We gotta go get Lem.
He doesn't show,
assume he made the deal.
They're gonna make you
give us up.
Shane?
Grenades.
El salvadorans.
The leader's missing.
His name is Guardo.
Start there.
We're gonna find out who did this,
and we're gonna kill 'em.
Why am I trusting you?
If you care about Guardo,
you'll play it my way.
Just let Nydia go.
She's how we're gonna get to Guardo.
You know, maybe he didn't do it, man.
- If it wasn't Guardo, who was it?
- Look at him, man!
Tilly, we know about you and Shane.
He's in the hospital.
You stepped out and now
you're spreading your legs for Shane?
Her old man got the drop on me.
Some black bitch called on your phone.
Is that who you're banging
while I got morning sickness?
Get out!
What do you know about
a guy named Hernan?
He's a Fed', undercover,
in a salvadoran organization.
Who are you?
We're on the same side.
Who are less in trouble,
the salvadorans or the mexicans?
I guess Guardo is collateral damage.
Prick blew up a friend of mine.
What, that cop? Guardo didn't do that.
The word came down. No distractions.
Shit, Guardo wasn't even up here then.
He was in Mexico with me.
Our son can never know what I've done.
I killed Lem.
Please forgive me. Please.
I can't... I can't do this anymore.
I'm sorry.
Please just ask me back.
Who's got it? Eye's up!
Nobody wants to talk.
Don't look at me!
Somebody's got it.
Can't do nothing in this place.
All right, ladies.
This ain't your first time at the dance.
You know the drill.
Drop 'em.
Oh, yeah, pretty boy.
You got a lot to think about.
Take your time.
Not you. Hurry up!
Come on, move!
I want your shoes.
I want your pants, your shirts.
Neat little piles.
Is he alone?
From the sound of it,
it's a do not disturb.
Yeah. Come in.
What is it, Benny?
You have a visitor, Antwon.
What does Rene look like here?
I know. I'm sorry.
I know my visitor can't be
half as fine as Rene.
Ain't that right, baby?
Better be right.
Some white cop from L.A.
He's pressing the warden
about seeing you right away.
Give me 2 shakes.
And shut that damn dog up.
Now I ain't got time for
sweet nothings, baby.
You gonna have to show me
what the good God gave you right now.
Come here.
My day just gets sunnier and sunnier.
How's life in prison?
Much better now
that Kavanaugh went down
for framing you.
Got my privileges back.
I didn't know we still
had business together.
You mean since my guy, who you put
a hit out on, got a grenade in his lap?
I heard about that.
Gotta give somebody points
for creativity.
Yeah. You.
I know you've been wanting
your pound of flesh from me,
waiting for Lem to come into jail.
But he ran, so you had your guys
on the outside find him, kill him.
Make it look salvadoran.
One time offer.
Tell me who it was
on the outside who offed Lem,
punishment will be limited to them.
You don't give me all
their names right now,
I will start tearing up
your gang from the outside
and I will start tearing
at your perks from the inside
and I promise you, I swear to God,
I will find a way,
no matter how many guards
you have on your payroll,
to get to you inside here.
And that, ladies and gentlemen,
is my final encore.
Making the great Vic Mackey
think I'm everyone...
and everywhere.
Responsible for all the
worst crimes against humanity.
It's sad, really.
You know, chasing ghosts
hasn't done you any favors.
I didn't off your boy.
Wished I did, and so do you.
'cause if you're
coming after me for this,
that means you lost...
your last clue.
Good seeing you, though.
He says, daddy, I got a boo-boo.
- Shane!
- But my boo-boo's on the inside.
- Oh!
- I talk to you later.
- When'd you get in, man?
- About 10 minutes ago.
We got a problem.
What?
Guardo didn't kill Lem.
No one in the salvadoran
organization did.
What?
Took a flyer at Antwon, too.
1-9ers are a no go.
We're back to square one.
No, Guardo's in a bunch of
charred pieces and crispy...
He didn't do it.
We got credible intel.
From who?
A federal I.C.E. agent
working undercover with the salvadorans.
So now the Fed's have the final say?
You know how many times
they've lied to us
to keep us from playing
in their backyard?
Doesn't feel like that.
So he's the rare Fed' that lies well.
Look, we finished this.
There's nothing more
to find out, all right?
Hey, Dutch, where are
we with Lem's case?
Holding pattern.
Still working on finding Guardo.
Guardo's a dead end.
I got it right from Hernan.
You met with Hernan?
I.C.E. Told me I couldn't get a sitdown.
What's the lab report say?
It's not back yet.
It's due.
I got a dead cop and no
suspect at the moment.
You think you could light
a fire under their bunsen burner?
Yeah. Maybe.
Yeah?
Did something happen last
weekend when you had Cassidy?
Something to upset her?
No. Why?
Well, she says she won't
stay with you next weekend
when I go to San Francisco
with Mattie and Megan
for the cure autism now rally.
Why not?
She doesn't want to talk about it.
I've already got the hotel reservations,
the plane tickets.
I'll talk to her.
Whatever it is, we'll fix it.
In the meantime,
I'm stuck here.
You think you could drive
Cassidy over here later?
She won't talk to you.
Well, that's not up to her.
I'll talk to you later.
We're running a list
of ex-military felons in the area.
Maybe they got Lem's grenade
from uncle Sam.
Uh, interesting reading?
Just checking out real estate prices.
Trying to see what this house
Mara and I are fixing up
is gonna be worth.
You wanna jump in
on this Lem thing anywhere?
It's a waste of time.
We settled this.
We can't be sure.
This I.C.E. agent,
he has no reason to lie to us.
You were sure enough to put a bullet
in Guardo before he confessed,
and I trusted you then
that we knew everything we were
ever going to know about that happened.
And you did what you had to do.
We all did.
Now just put this
in the rearview mirror.
Stop asking questions that
there are no answers to.
Whatever funk he was in seems over.
He seems at peace with it.
I don't know how I can be
until I know for sure.
When we took down that stash of grenades
the night that Lem died,
Shane did the con solo, right?
Vic, come on.
Did you see anything weird that night?
About Lem? The night...
No. No.
He did say, um...
When Kavanaugh's frameup job was going
and things looked really bad,
he said something like...
What if he said he had
a grenade from the bust
and he was with Lem and
it went off accidentally?
I just took it as him
want to lie to get you off.
What did you say?
I said it wouldn't help
and he'd be admitting
aiding and abetting.
What did he say?
Nothing.
You don't remember Shane's count
on grenades that night?
Not here. At the salvadoran house?
Jesus, Vic, I don't want
to think like that.
Do you rember the count or not?
Write it down.
What do you have?
73, like the home run record.
We gotta run a check.
What are we saying here?
All we're saying is...
As soon as we can...
The first chance you get,
you... you're gonna...
quietly confirm
that Shane logged in 73 grenades
and that all 73 grenades are still
sitting there nice and neat
in the bomb squad
evidence locker.
Transcript : Swsub.com
Synchro : Artusamak
Chasing Ghosts
Morning.
Mind if I take one of these?
Was this Lem's?
I'm sorry. I didn't...
No, no, no. It's all right.
You're part of the team now.
No reason it should go empty.
Trust me. If i'm wrong,
I'll buy you a beer.
Hey, there, gentlemen.
Well, someone had a good night.
Pregnancy sex is the best kind.
Give you something to look forward to.
Thanks. I'll give Mara a call.
Just the crew I'm looking for.
Got a body in an apartment
building on colby.
Young woman. 20. Stabbed.
We taking straight up homicides now?
Victim's Emily Martin.
Daughter of the city
controller Robert Martin.
The guy that's got his fingers
on the city's purse strings.
That's our special touch.
A lot of people will be watching.
Aceveda called himself
to ask for extra manpower.
Just rember who you work for.
These high profile cases
are just one big invitation
to get ass reamed by the bosses.
So let's get it done
and get out of the spotlight.
Let's try not to get ass reamed.
Well, it wasn't a robbery.
The extent of the wounds?
Someone gave her an O.J. shave.
A long way from daddy's wave of power.
Maybe she got tired
of the west side.
You guys know the drill.
Look for nosy neighbors.
Something there.
Maybe a shoe print.
Good work, eagle eye.
I knew they bumped him up for a reason.
Come on. Let's start over here.
Police. Open up.
Hey, there's the poster girl.
Looking good, Tina.
Bow down to the poster girl.
Man, I guess wet dreams
can come true.
Hey, how you doing?
I'm good. How are you?
Good. I called you a couple of times.
Is everything copacetic?
Yeah. Well, you heard
about the transfer.
They basically wanted me
in some P.R. role.
talking in schools,
recruitment meetings, things like that.
You mean the poster.
Yeah, that's all that was.
But I got to meet a couple of
people up at the chief's office
and convinced 'em that I could represent
the force better out in the streets.
Well, I think you belong here.
Dutch, there's a woman in the lobby
who wants to talk to a detective.
Uh, Steve's free.
She said actually
that it's about Guardo Lima.
That's your suspect
in Lem's murder case, right?
Uh, yeah. Excuse me.
Tina, welcome back.
We should talk about
your new assignment.
Ok.
You heard that Julian's
on the Strike Team, yeah?
Yeah. Yeah.
So who am I riding with?
Well, for now, me.
Is that a problem?
No, no. You're a Sergeant now,
and Sergeants don't get out that much.
That's ok. I'm gonna keep you real busy.
It's only temporary.
You have information about Guardo Lima?
He's missing. Something bad's happened.
When was the last time you spoke to him?
He hasn't called me in over a week.
Well, that doesn't necessarily
mean anything's wrong.
We talk every day. He loves me.
No one has seen or heard from him.
Was it Salseda?
Who's Salseda.
A mexican. He's the one who wanted
to take over the business Guardo ran.
That cop knows all about it.
He's the one who told me
that Salseda wanted to kill Guardo.
OK, which cop?
I'm the one they had
in protective custody,
so don't pretend you don't
know what i'm talking about.
Kevin Hiatt, this is
Robert and Patricia Martin.
Kevin's heading up the team
that's doing the investigation.
I'm sorry about your loss.
Thank you.
The Martins are friends
of the department
and I told them I'd be their go-between.
Emily was a beautiful,
wonderful young woman.
Do you know what she was
doing in this part of town?
Our daughter didn't deserve this,
and my wife doesn't deserve
to be put through anything else.
Of course.
Give me a second.
The Martins are dealing with a tragedy.
Lots of people might try
to paint this a certain way,
so we can't let anybody
sully this girl's reputation.
Yeah, sure.
Hey, witness says he saw
his neighbor Rahid Moore
hurrying out carrying 2 trash bags.
6 flights up, he still took the stairs.
People say he's loud.
Gets visitors all night long.
When they've asked him to keep it down,
he's made threats.
Apartment's right over here.
Let's pay a visit.
- Uh, Vic?
- What's the problem?
Aceveda and the old man want us
to keep the daughter clean.
We don't even know
what we're supposed to be hiding yet.
Hiding, hmm?
I'll help you figure that out.
Just keep it to yourself for now.
Look, city controller on one side,
Claudette's moral code on the other.
So whoever you screw, you
get cut off at the knees.
Fantastic.
Trust me. There's a way out.
There always is.
First we find out the truth.
Then we figure out what to do.
Late night visitors
means late night customers.
He packed up his stash
and got out of dodge.
If Rahid had a parking spot,
the building will have his plate.
I'll get it on the wire.
Anything?
Think so.
Phone numbers. Good.
Call 'em in. See if you can get
some names to go with those numbers.
Hey, Vic. Found this under the bed.
Guy must have need a boost for the road.
Or daddy's little girl did.
They came and got me one
night about a week ago.
Took me to this safe house
'cause they told me I was in danger.
From Salseda?
I just want to find Guardo.
Could you look for him? Please?
He's supposed to be in Mexico, isn't he?
The main one said that Salseda
would try to kidnap me
to get leverage on Guardo.
And then they'd just, what, let you go?
This one? He said that Guardo
never came back to L.A.,
that they caught Salseda.
Then he dropped me off.
They know what happened to Guardo.
They know if someone killed him.
Her time frame puts all this
during Vic's personal days off.
I understand the time frame.
Vic had Guardo on the phone.
Nydia confirms it.
And there's no Salseda
in the department's records
with any connection with the
salvadorans or the cartel.
We are not gonna accuse Mackey
of murder and be wrong again.
Let me put Vic in the room with her.
I'll set it up as a surprise,
but I'll let the camera roll.
You shook that hornet's nest once.
Haven't you been stung enough yet?
It's not an accusation,
and if the girl's lying,
what's the harm?
Keep it contained.
Good. I'll keep Billings out of it.
Rahid Moore. How do we find him?
I don't know anyone by that name.
That's right. You're the
P.T.A. mom from eagle rock.
Husband, two kids.
Weird we found your number
in Rahid's apartment
on the shity side of the freeway.
The guy with two distribution arrests.
Had three stars by your name.
Your husband know you're on the spike?
I don't know what you're talking about.
- Bitch to hide, ain't it?
- Hey!
Got to work real hard
to hide that secret.
Stop!
Let me see.
Where you shoot up, on your ankle?
- Between the toes?
- Get off me!
Tell me where to find Rahid.
Stop.
I'm getting to the good part.
Whew. Nice scab marks.
Your husband knows.
Otherwise, you're one frustrated gal
when it comes to
the oral pleasures of life.
Stop it.
Then tell me what I need to know.
Don't tell Jeffrey?
I'm gonna tell him,
your kids, your friends.
I'm even gonna tell the little old lady
who brings the cookies
to the P.T.A. meetings.
Sure is getting hot in here.
OK. Hey, hey. This stops now,
you understand?
What?
This Tina bullshit.
This isn't high school.
You know, that's too bad,
because I heard she was gonna ask
you to the sadie hawkins dance.
Hey, how's the quick
meter business going?
The machines are still here,
which means you're still
lining your pocket
on the department's dime, right?
I've been waiting for you
to throw it in my face.
I'm gonna do more than that.
I'm gonna throw it in I.A.D.'s face.
Why, 'cause I gave you
a little jab about Tina?
Yes.
But I'll make you a deal.
You get those machines
out of here today,
you back off the Tina
and me thing forever,
and I'll pretend it never happened.
Remember that real partner vibe
we had going catching the runway rapist?
That had a shelf life
of about what, 48 hours?
- What's I.A.D.'s number again?
- All right.
All right.
But this is gonna take some doing.
Now I have to cover my ass
for the rest of the day.
You guys ever think about
putting some doors in here?
You're in charge. See what you can do.
What now?
He texts me back with
a number and a time.
Each number means
a different location.
How long before he answers?
It depends on when he can meet.
And your P.T.A. schedule.
I just don't understand
where this is supposed to go.
All the numbers
are right there in the file.
Just look it up. Hey, Kevin.
Hi, Danny.
This is Tina Hanlon.
- Poster girl, right?
- Yes.
Yeah. I'm Kevin Hiatt.
Nice to meet you. Tina.
Nice to meet you.
Tina, did you finish that filing yet?
It's a three week job.
What do you think?
You know, I'm your superior.
When you talk to me, lose the tone.
You thought it was tough with Julian,
you ain't seen nothing yet.
You've got to find a way
to be better than you were.
Otherwise, you're gonna end up
being our permanent filing girl.
When I was gone, I met a few
people in some high places,
so I'm not exactly knocked
over by the new stripes.
I'm not a trainee here anymore.
I'll watch my tongue, but so will you.
Or what?
Or you'll have to explain
why you can't get along
with the new face of the department.
Hey, sweetheart.
Everything ok, kiddo?
Hey.
You know what?
Let's go upstairs.
All right, Cass.
What's going on?
I don't have to talk to him.
Look, you're causing your mom
a lot of stress here, sweetie.
Mattie and Megan have
a beautiful weekend planned
with a bunch of kids just like...
I could stay with Falovia.
Her parents said it's fine.
Hey, you're staying with me.
Or not.
Let's talk about what's bothering you.
Fine.
My friend Brian, his dad's a lawyer,
did a "Lexis/Exis" search on you.
I saw all the shit you've done.
What?
The brutality complaints.
The I.A.D. guy thought
you killed people.
Oh, Cassidy.
Listen to me.
People say things and write things.
That does mean that they're true, ok?
That I.A.D. cop got caught
trying to frame your father.
He's the one in jail now.
I don't want to learn
about life from you.
You have nothing to teach me.
Hey, I'll teach you some respect.
Respect,
is earned.
Cassidy...
Whatever you've read,
whatever you've heard,
it's not the whole truth, honey.
Like the baby you had
with some other woman?
I heard mom taking on
the phone with grandma.
She didn't know I was awake.
Cassidy...
That's adult stuff.
You don't have to concern
yourself with that right now.
You kept a secret that I have
some baby brother i've never even seen?
Vic, Rahid answered the text message.
We got a location.
- Vic?
- What?
Somebody upstairs say
they've got information on Guardo Lima.
What kind of information?
I had trouble following it.
You know that world better than I do.
I'm buried. Can you talk to him?
I'm kind of busy right now.
Well, if it's about Lemansky's
murder, it could be important.
Hey, Vic, let's go.
I got a location on a murder suspect.
If they're still around when I get back,
i'll chat 'em up then.
Valerie couldn't make it,
but she sends her regards.
You want to tell us why you ran out
of your apartment with 2 trash bags?
Don't you dump your trash?
Not the day after pickup.
That's when the bins is empty.
Emily Martin. She was in
your apartment today.
Never heard of her.
So when her blood comes back
off the bottom of your shoe,
you gonna tell us
you never stepped in it?
You stabbed her, then
you ran out and dumped the knife,
and Johnnie Cochran ain't
alive to represent you.
Do you know who this girl was, man?
You mean her daddy?
Yeah.
Some big, important city dude.
Vips get quick police response.
Now, we're gonna hand over
his daughter's killer,
and they're gonna make
an example out of you.
I let her suck my dick. So what?
That sure as hell
don't mean I killed her.
Aside from your winning personality,
is there any other reason why Emily
would want to play head games with you?
She need fuel for the needle.
Didn't have the money
to keep herself mellow,
so she started paying another dude
with some mouth and pussy.
What dude?
Snail. He moved some shit
for me over in Brentwood.
I brought her around a couple times.
What can I say?
The girl was smart enough
to cut out the middleman
and go directly to the source.
How did snail feel about that?
White boy's a control freak.
He got on the shit,
then started rationing it out.
Thought he could keep
the pussy on a leash.
You see him kill Emily?
I heard something.
By the time I got outside,
she was already done.
And I knew y'all was gonna be
crawling all over the place,
so I stuck my stash in the
trash and stepped outside.
Pat yourself on the back later.
Right now you're gonna tell us
where Snail is.
Right?
I'll tell you something else.
That girl...
She had no love for her pops.
What's the latest
with the Martin murder?
Getting to a dark place.
Meaning?
The daughter was
a heroin addicted whore.
Paid for her drugs with
pussy and mouth favors.
Other than that, she was
pippi longstocking.
That's a lot to get between.
He's a friend
of the department's, but...
But if this thing's uncontrollable,
there's no sense in you
getting burned, too.
We need to appear loyal.
But if the press gets ahold of the
information, that's out of our control.
Martin can have somewhere
else to focus his anger.
Someone's gotta take the heat, right?
Anything I should know about?
Nothing we can't handle.
Don't let these people influence you.
Follow the case where it leads.
The VIP key's only
gonna open so many door.
You got it?
Now's the time to be taking notes.
- Hey, Vic.
- Excuse me.
Shane logged in 73 grenades
that night just like we rembered.
You talked to the bomb squad?
It seemed like a paperwork thing.
Had a rookie count 'em all by hand.
73. All accounted for.
Oh shit. You know I'm an asshole,
first I doubt of Lem, now Shane.
I'm a complete asshole, man.
No, we just wanted answers.
This is a good one to get.
Maybe Shane's right.
Maybe we got all the
answers we're gonna have.
Hey, Danny, got a minute?
Of course.
What's up?
My daughter knows about Lee.
Oh, Jesus.
How?
She heard Corrine talking on the phone.
Look, no offense,
but she may be your ex,
but that lady's been
a real pain in my ass.
Now, look, Vic, I chose
to do this alone for a reason, ok?
I don't need a hassle around here.
This isn't people in the barn.
This is my daughter.
Yeah, well, I never wanted you
to get involved.
Not you, not your ex,
not your kids.
I've learned as a parent
that things don't go as we planned.
Do they?
So now what?
Vic and I got the front.
You guys come in
from around the back.
Ok, let's go.
Wait. Wait, wait!
What?
Shit!
That's a .45.
These vests aren't
gonna be worth shit.
Hit it!
Go!
Get down!
Hiatt, I got him!
Don't move!
Are you hit?
No.
I'm not hit.
Bitch!
I'm taking this guy in alone.
What?
You know the situation.
There's no way you can
walk away from it clean.
So screw.
What the hell's the city controller
even do, anyway?
Eliminates the Strike Team
with the stroke of a pen.
This guy took shots
at both you and Hiatt.
Shane's right.
We can't walk the guy into the cage
who took shots at cops
without messing up his hair some.
It sends a bad message.
Martin's a friend of the department.
That means more money, more cops,
so we have to consider it.
Look, the Captain said
we didn't have to worry about that.
She doesn't have all the pieces.
We got the suspect.
Let's just take this guy in.
That's what I'm gonna do.
I'm just doing it alone.
No! I'm not comfortable with that.
Look, we're gonna get
squeezed whatever we do.
Maybe I can figure a way around it.
But if not, I'll take the hit.
For the rest of us? Why?
Because I'm out of here
at the end of the month.
There's nothing else they can do to me.
Listen, maybe I should take him in.
Look, you guys all have
something to lose.
Now, maybe there's a
compromise to be worked out,
but you guys aren't the
ones to be compromised.
He needs to show up back at the barn
looking the same way he looks now.
Won't mess up a hair on his little head.
You brought the knife.
You followed the girl.
Death penalty's a slam dunk.
I can make it so
you could avoid all that.
Maybe even see the light of day again.
What are you talking about?
You know who Emily's father is?
Well, the family wants
to avoid embarrassment.
You just gotta be willing
to tell the right story.
Yeah? What's the right story?
Good boy.
Detroit, bring him up to interrogation.
How'd you like to walk out
of here with no charges?
I'd like that very much.
Step around. I'll tell you how.
Hey, you're back.
Any word on the lab results?
They promised me by
the end of business day.
Uh, that woman's still here.
What woman?
The one with information on Guardo Lima.
Oh, right.
She's stuck around this long.
Uh... Yeah. Ok.
Thanks. She's in interrogation one.
Got it.
Guardo never came back.
Guardo's a mysterious guy.
Did you do something to him?
I never even saw him.
What happened to Salseda?
He must have got away.
I heard from people in Mexico.
They said Guardo came back to L.A.
I heard the same thing.
I only wish I'd caught him.
I don't understand.
We heard a rumor that
Salseda wanted to kill Guardo.
We didn't know if it was true but,
Guardo was a suspect in the murder
of a cop, so I didn't give a shit.
So you lied to me?
You kept me prisoner?
No. I told you you could
leave whenever you wanted.
The smart thing was to stay.
All the stuff Guardo did,
it's only a matter of time.
You're lucky he didn't
drag you down with him.
Why don't we just get
Kavanaugh out of jail?
Have me investigated again?
Witness protection?
Sounds more like kidnapping to me.
All right,
I wanted Guardo.
I heard about Salseda on the street,
so I used it.
I would have used
anything I had to get him,
to bring him in for Lem's death.
But the mexicans got to him first.
You did all this based on a rumor?
Yeah, I did.
If I had ignored that rumor
and Nydia had got killed by that guy,
you'd be asking me a lot
tougher questions right now.
So you never found Guardo?
- No, I...
- She seems convinced you did.
For all we know,
Guardo could have sent her here
to make us think that he's dead,
just to throw us off his track.
Oh, for Christ sake.
She's in love with a guy
who blows up kids for a living.
You're trying to show people
why you should stay.
This escapade looks like
another reason why you should go.
Guardo was killed by the mexicans.
You don't believe me, talk to Hernan.
Tell me how to contact him and I will.
I'll close the books on the
girlfriend's false accusations.
Ask Hiatt.
You caught the man that killed Emily?
Yeah.
I think you know what your
daughter was into when she died.
She was an addict.
I tried to help her, but
she wouldn't take it so I cut her off.
I thought it would keep her
from buying more.
Do you know what your daughter
was doing to get her drugs?
She threw it in my face,
trying to get more money from me.
Well, it was all true.
But that's not how history has to read.
Thank you.
I mean, there are some
things I can't fake.
The M.E.'s gonna find
that heroin in her system.
I'll take care of that.
I've got an appeals hearing
in a couple of weeks.
They're going to decide
whether to force me out or not.
Well, I'll see what I can do.
Must be good to be king.
Snail dealt for me a little.
He was in over his head.
Told me about this girl
that was trying to
get him out of the life.
Shame.
Just trying to get him
to stop selling drugs.
Guess she was a real nice girl.
Emily found out I was dealing,
she wanted me to quit.
She followed me up to Rahid's apartment,
trying to stop me from buying.
Kept pressing me hard in the elevator.
I just lost it.
She didn't deserve any of it.
What's the problem?
We shouldn't be playing God.
God creates all men equal.
Once they get out of the womb,
he starts playing favorites.
Is that Lem's
lab report?
Is it?
Yeah, and the final autopsy report.
And?
Nothing much. No fingerprints.
No DNA left behind.
Well, let me see it.
You think there's anyone
who wants to solve Lem's murder
more than me?
There's crime scene photos
and autopsy photos.
Curtis was eviscerated
from the waist down.
Give me it.
What report is this?
This is new.
That's Kavanaugh's last report.
Part of the deal he made
when he came clean about you
was providing full disclosure.
Hey, Kev, can I ask you something?
Absolutely.
Hey.
Hey, Dutch.
Hey, Tina. That project I gave you,
you made a couple mistakes.
Come on. I'll show you before I leave.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
- See ya.
- Bye.
Did you ever ask me about Hernan,
that I.C.E. agent in the
salvadoran organization?
Sure.
Did you guys get in touch with him?
- Yeah.
- How?
It's easier to negotiate
between Federal Agencies.
But, you're not a Federal Agent anymore.
No. No, not anymore.
Careful with that.
It's a sophisticated piece of machinery.
I don't want to see any dings in it.
I gave it some thought.
If you want to keep the machines,
go ahead.
Why, so you'll still have it
to hand over my head?
Yeah, that's right.
No, thanks. I'll pass.
I can keep the leverage
or you can lose the money.
It's your call.
Hey, guys?
Hang on a second.
Hey, Cassidy. Come on in.
This is Lee.
What's his whole name?
Lee carson sofer.
Carson's my mom's maiden name.
What's his birthday?
On the second. 6:19 A.M.
Do you want to hold him?
Everything
all right, Cass?
No, I... I don't want to hold him.
I just want to see.
That's ok.
Another time.
Hey.
Vic wants the three of us to meet.
When?
Right now.
Portillo Auto Body.
He wants to walk Lem's crime scene
the time of night that it happened.
See if there's anything
the lab boys missed.
Lab report came in?
Yeah.
Anything useful?
I don't think so.
You wanna ride together?
I got to finish this paperwork
on our stabbing.
I'll be five minutes behind you.
Cool. I'll, uh...
See you there.
Ok.
Vic: Yeah?
He's on his way.
Good.
You sure you don't want me to be there?
No. Keep your distance.
Ok.
Hey.
Wanna wait for Ronnie or what?
No. We can get started.
Ok.
Read the report.
Yeah? What'd it say?
Nothing new.
No prints.
No forensics.
Guardo was smart.
He was careful.
Not careful enough to escape us.
No, not that.
Guardo didn't kill Lem.
I tortured him, shot him, and burned
his body, and he didn't kill Lem.
We were right there with you.
Yeah.
I know.
But Guardo didn't do it.
Salvadorans, they wanted
to stay off our radar.
They didn't even kill Emolia
when they found out that she'd snitched.
Well, maybe some
salvadoran rogue banger...
What, who killed Lem with a grenade,
let no trace, and
disappeared like a ghost?
I don't think so.
It wasn't 1-9ers
looking for Antwon revenge.
Made a fool of myself up
at Lompoc finding that one out.
So I asked Ronnie
to check if you logged all the grenades
that night at the bust.
He counted 73 at the house,
and there are 73 sitting there in the,
bomb squad evidence locker right now.
Which means...
You pocketed a grenade
before Aceveda even lied to us
about Lem ratting us out?
You lied to us at the bust
about the count, you...
Before I even started
to question Lem,
you were looking
for a way to shut him up
to make it look salvadoran?
Don't even go there, man.
You were the last one
to get to the meet.
You couldn't lose your tail, right?
- That's right.
- Well, did you try?
As much as I could.
I couldn't look too suspicious,
remember?
Kavanaugh wrote another report.
Part of his deal.
He was short-handed that night.
Just him and one other guy.
Stop right there, Vic.
There's nothing good
in where you're going...
Just him and one other guy.
So he followed me and Ronnie.
So what? What did...
You dropped a grenade in his lap?
What did you do, just run?
I did what I thought
had to be done at the time.
Oh, God.
I know, man.
I know.
- Oh...
- I know.
Oh...
You piece of shit!
You made that decision
on your own?
He wouldn't go to Mexico.
Oh!
I told him about the goat farm.
About the way out.
About the money that we
were going to send him.
You said that if he wouldn't
take the ride to Mexico,
that we would know that he turned.
- He didn't turn!
- I know that now.
We said that we would look him
in the eye and we would have the truth.
And he never turned on us.
We couldn't afford to take that chance.
You think this has been easy for me?
Carrying all this alone?
For you? Lem!
It was an impossible situation.
At the time, it was either
him or the rest of us.
Bullshit!
Look, I was protecting
you and ronnie from it.
Look, if he would have gone to jail
like he wanted,
he would have been
killed by Antwon
or turned by Kavanaugh.
Man, you know that.
I don't know that.
He was strong.
You killed him because you were scared.
He was strong and you were a coward!
I was being strong for all of us,
and I am not a coward.
Yeah, you were.
You were when you sat by
and watched me tear Guardo
apart for something you did.
Jesus Christ, what did you turn me into?
He's an asshole murder.
I'm not an executioner!
Well, go tell that to Terry's family.
That's different.
That son of a bitch, he was a traitor.
Lem was my friend.
He was mine, too.
Look, you think you're looking
at me through some window.
And all you're really doing
is looking in a mirror.
You and I, we're nothing alike.
I would never...
Oh, you did. More than once.
So let's at least tell the truth now.
Lem's gone.
I would have spared Lem.
And I stepped up and put Lem down
so you could go to bed
at night believing that.
You didn't come to me.
You didn't talk to me.
We didn't decide, and now it's too late.
There was no time.
I didn't know if Kavanaugh
was going to swoop down
and pick us up at any second.
If you weren't sure...
If you weren't sure,
you should have taken that chance
that he was still with us.
You owed him that chance!
I had to kill my friend,
and you know why.
Look, it's taken me a while,
but you're gonna learn
how to accept it, man.
I will never accept that!
I'm not gonna fight you.
Ronnie's not even coming, is he?
What, you told him you were
gonna look me in the eye,
find out the truth?
Are you so god damn psychic?
Why didn't you know
that Aceveda was lying about Lem, huh?
I mean, all I was doing
was following your game plan, coach.
You killed my friend.
Then you almost let
Kavanaugh send me away for it.
I never would have let it come to that.
You let me kill Guardo
without opening your god damn mouth!
I had the change to pull the
trigger on you once before.
I didn't do it,
and Lem lost his life because of it.
Lem would have broken.
I took it on myself
the way that you took it off of us
for Terry.
Vic, you're gonna learn
to be ok with it.
Man, you just need a little time.
You and me, we're all out of time.
Lem's case is still open.
I hope they catch you.
I hope they do.
I hope everybody knows what you did.
You don't get to do
what you did for free.
You're gonna pay that bill.
What, you gonna give Dutch
a little push in my direction?
Well, maybe when they got me,
they'll have a little time to look
into who killed Terry.
That's old business,
and all you got is hearsay.
Our entire lives are hearsay, Vic.
All the shit we've done.
And I've got a hell of a lot more
on you than you've got on me.
Get in your truck. Drive away.
Leave here before I kill you.
No, you won't.
We've already been through all that.
Before?
You didn't blow lem
in half with a grenade.
I see you again, I will kill you.
God damn hypocrite.