A greedy man
once yearned for more,
so the fool began to borrow.
He ate and drank
and told the bank,
"I'll pay the debt tomorrow."
But as both dolt
and purse grew fat,
the calendar grew thinner.
The debt collector had enough
and hungered for his dinner.
The coward ran,
with coin in hand,
but come dawn, lost his breath.
The fool was caught,
'twas all for naught,
for the collector's name
was Death.
Heck of a poem there, fella.
I just caught the tail end.
You got any more chilling verses
in that book of yours?
Oh, this isn't
a poetry book, cowboy‐man.
This is a ledger of debts.
Debts to be paid
in money or blood,
and lately, Venmo.
I've been sent
to collect in blood.
Don't do this!
I have a wife
and two young mistresses,
also a secret other wife.
Please, I'm a good man.
A good man!
In my experience, Mr. Texan...
there's no such thing
as a good man.
♪ There were ninety and nine
that safely lay ♪
♪ In the shelter of the fold ♪
♪ Of the fold ♪
♪ But one was out
on the hills away ♪
♪ Far off from
the gates of gold ♪
♪ Gates of gold ♪
♪ Away on the mountain
wild and bare ♪
♪ Away from
the tender shepherd's care. ♪
Mm, as pristine
as the Garden of Eden
before Eve came along.
Homer Simpson?
I didn't know you were a fellow
volunteer Litter Gitter?
No, I'm doing community service
'cause of where I told the judge
to shove some parking tickets.
Well, sir,
I guess your punishment
is my predilection to do good.
Oh, Flanders, you do
so much for the town,
yet no one ever
appreciates you for it.
Why, thank you, Homer.
Not a compliment.
Saying you're dumb.
Shucks!
Gosh! Ah!
Honey, ooh, mustard!
Hey, that's a strange place
to check your bag‐a‐rino.
Dear Lord.
Crap, crap, crap,
crap, crap, crap,
crap! Oof!
I saw you fell,
so I rushed over
to laugh at you, then...
Aw, it's always been my dream
to find a bag of money.
You stole my dream.
You know, I'd say it's all
a part of God's plan,
but usually that only applies
to horrible tragedies.
Aw, a do‐gooder like you
finding this money
is proof that karma is real,
which sucks
'cause now I can't club you
over the head and take it.
Aw, thanks, neighbor.
$173,296.
We should get a huge terrarium
with like a million turtles.
No, we should get a speedboat
with bunk beds on it.
‐Turtles.
‐Bunk‐boat.
‐Turtles!
‐Bunk‐boat!
I wish your great‐grandfather,
Paw Paw Flanders,
was still here to guide us.
He was the finest man
I ever knew.
Pouch of chewing tobacco
for myself
and a pouch of candy tobacco
for my grandson.
Paw Paw, that man stole
a loaf of bread.
It's under his T‐shirt
that says...
Linda Ronstadt.
Stay here, Neddy.
Afternoon, mop top.
Yeah?
Here's some "bread"
for your bread,
my countercultural friend.
‐Have a good one.
‐Death to pigs, except you, man.
Gee, Paw Paw,
why didn't you arrest him?
Neddy, when I was growing up
at the orphanage,
the nuns taught us one thing:
the harder the good,
the better the man.
Boys, I know just what to do.
Oh, my gosh.
In all my years
of orphanagereal management,
I've never seen
a donation this generous.
The town's gonna go
ape over bananas
when it hears all about
your generosity.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I always donate anonymously.
"When thou doest thine alms..."
"Do not sound a trumpet
before thee."
Matthew 6:2.
Aw, but wouldn't you like
some accolades
and attaboys for being
such an upstanding fella?
Oh, I don't do good deeds
for recognition.
That's why no one
ever gives it to me.
Hold on.
What if you donated that money
in the name of someone special?
I could honor my Paw Paw.
Oh, see?
Nothing prideful about that.
Now, what's the name
of the saintly fella
you'd like to give
all the credit to?
Ned Flanders.
Uh, the First.
Ned's number one!
Paw Paw was technically
Ned number one,
so that chant's okay with me.
So, how does it feel to be the
most beloved man in Springfield?
You mean, the grandson of?
It feels darn‐diddly good.
I love a pomegranate.
Its juices remind me of the
bloody profession I've chosen.
No, I agree, it's not subtle.
Anyhoo, the Rich Texan account
has been balanced,
and I'll be bringing you
the proof.
No, not the whole head.
They only let you have
one bag on United.
An anonymous do‐gooder donated
a fortune to a local orphanage,
money found
in an old Pan Am bag.
A grand total of $173,296.
I'm staying in Springfield.
I have a very old,
very personal debt to collect.
I spoke to the generous donor,
who insisted on anonymity.
It feels darn‐diddly good.
Good day to you, shopkeep.
Quite the collection
of funny books you have here.
Wonder if you could help us.
Looking for a local fella,
name of Flanders.
Do I look like the town's
information kiosk to you?
It is much smaller than I.
Hit the bricks, Lucky Charms.
I like a good joke.
But my partner?
She's not quite as jovial.
- ‐Now, where's this Flanders chap?
- ‐
Ooh, locking the door
as a means of intimidation.
How original.
The silent
but violent accomplice,
another overworked cliché.
Correction, French accomplice.
An unexpected yet still
underwhelming twist.
Two stars.
Just point us towards
Ned Flanders,
and Colette won't have to spoil
this lovely morning
we're having.
Mando!
Stop, stop! I don't know
where Flanders lives,
but you can always find him at
the First Church of Springfield.
Now, that wasn't
so hard, was it?
I'll let you get back to your
Heathcliffs and your Garfields.
I only like the cat ones.
Um, two thugs just manhandled me
in the collectibles.
Why the hell am I
paying you for protection?
If another outfit
is moving in on my town,
then appropriate violence
will be taken.
Bye, now.
Mr. Flanders, it's an honor
to live next door
to such a generous man.
Baller move, Ned.
You splashed the cash
on some no‐dads,
and now you're the top
God‐wad. Respect.
Well, I can't accept
your praise,
as that donation
wasn't in my name.
Oh, you heard him, kids.
Take back your praise.
Anonymous Boy Scout Superman
doesn't want any hugs
or handshakes
or little pats on the head.
Well, I wasn't trying to‐‐
Um, oops.
I forgot my Bible inside. Bye.
Uh, pardon me, sir.
I believe that's my good book
you're giving a look.
"Ned Flanders."
Used to be a man had to die
to get his name
printed in his Bible.
Eh, guess I saved someone
the trouble.
Hey, haven't seen you
in our church before.
Are you new to the pew?
I am a debt collector by trade,
and this ledger
is my "good book."
I only have one unbalanced debt,
my very first.
It's like having a tickle
in my nose for 50 years
but never getting to sneeze.
That's the same amount I‐‐
This is now your debt to me.
Uncle Neddy!
Barb, am I glad to see you.
You know, I was just
talking to...
He's gone.
No, I'm not.
I started to hide, but I
couldn't find any good places.
I'll see you later.
That was the most terrifying
man I ever met.
Yup, he's an odd duck,
all right.
Say, I'm glad I found you.
The Springfield Winter Markets
are opening tonight,
and I was pondering if you
wanted to come with.
To chaperone the kids?
To chaperone me.
Like a date.
Ooh!
Get out of town.
You? A javelin thrower?
Oh, yeah. I would've qualified
for the Pine City
Junior Throwlympics, but,
you know, that was
the year the good Lord
thought to bless me
with my top shelf here.
I hated to hang up
my javelin clogs,
but luckily I discovered
my true passion:
parentless children.
Barb Belfry, at the risk
of sounding crass,
I... I think you're swell.
Cute couple alert.
So cute, so cute!
Some arm candy for Flandy.
Whoop‐de‐do.
Uh, you've had
a little too much eggnog.
Nog just gives voice to truth.
That's right, neighborino.
I'm onto you.
When you bought
all the orphans in town,
I thought you were a fool,
but now I see what you
really did with that money:
buy the love and admiration
of all these suckers.
Boo!
All right, noggy,
into the drunk rink with you.
Go slip it off.
I've never been so humiliated
at a seasonal market.
How can someone else's
generosity make you angry?
Mm, because that money
should've been mine!
I fall down inclines
all the time,
and all I ever get
is concussionezzezzezzezzes...
zzezzes.
Wow. I can't believe I'm married
to the most selfish man
in the world.
How come every song you play
has to be so kooky and obscure?
Just for once, I wouldn't mind
a little Taylor Swift
before we commit an atrocity.
It's right here.
Relax. I remember it.
Evergreen Terrace.
740... something.
Hmm?
What do you got there, boy?
Drop it, boy. Drop it.
Doggy man face.
Nighty night, Mr. Flanders.
Well, as the picture frame
said to the level,
that was quite an even‐ing.
Oh, this was
the best night I've had
in a month of Sundays.
Barb, if I were
to kiss you right now,
would, uh, would that
be all right?
Golly, it sure would.
Hot dog!
Well, bye.
Ned, would you like to come in
and see my javelin medals?
‐Oh, yeah. Oh, you betcha.
‐ Diddly.
‐That's the business.
‐Doodly.
‐Oh, good golly, Miss Molly.
‐Great golly.
Right in the kisser.
Oh, yeah.
Is that... is that Sideshow Mel?
You must be a real fan.
Well, I used to be.
He's your husband?
Well, technically,
but don't you worry, hon.
We got an arrangement,
me and Mel.
What?!
I get to have
my extracurriculars
and, uh, so does he.
Well, he tries, anyway.
Aw, bless his heart.
Oh, Lordy, I'm an adulterer.
Don't mind me.
Just rebooting the Wi‐Fi.
Gah, the cuckold!
Oh, come on, Mel. You knew
I had the living room tonight.
Check the darn schedule.
Don't worry about him.
He can turn his video game
up real loud.
Barb Belfry,
this diddly‐daliance
is doodily.
done.
Another Craigslist winner?
Oh, shut up, Mel.
Your prized piggy,
Mr. Ned Flanders.
This is not Ned Flanders.
W‐Well, sure it is.
Why, look at his credit cards,
his medic alert bracelet,
the tag on his suspiciously
tight undershirt.
They‐they all say Ned Flanders.
Stupid Flanders,
getting me kidnapped.
You've brought me the wrong man!
Okay, okay,
I'll just get rid of him.
Don't kill him.
Yet.
It's your lucky day, big boy.
I hope you like HGTV.
This one loves
the Property Brothers.
Giant charmless goons.
Oh, Lord, seems like
everything's gone screwy
ever since I donated
that money in my name‐‐
I mean, in, uh, Paw Paw's name.
Oh, are you punishing me
for one small,
possibly prideful moment?
God?
Not quite, church chum,
but another friend of yours
is on the line.
Flanders, you got to save me.
This guy's way too weird
not to be dangerous.
He doesn't even look
at his phone when he's bored.
He's not human, I tell you.
You've got 24 hours
to get me my money,
or I'll take out his tonsils
with a power drill.
No cops.
Ned, Homer's missing.
I just found the back door open,
his car's in the garage,
and the dog looks really queasy
for some reason.
The last thing I said to Homer
was that he was the
most selfish man in the world.
Do you think
I should call the police?
Oh, no. If she calls the police,
Homer's dead.
If I want to save his life,
I have to... tell a lie.
Uh, H‐Homer, uh, uh,
stopped by here last night
and apologized
for being a jerk to me,
and‐and, uh, you know,
then he hopped on a bus
to Shelbyville
for a‐a‐a three‐day
anger management course
at the Airport, uh,
Hyatt‐Hyatt Express.
That doesn't sound like Homer.
Are you calling me a liar?!
No, but if anyone other than you
told me that story,
I'd be a little suspicious.
Oh, you got to believe
old Honest Ned.
Anyway, I'm, uh, late for my,
uh... hormone therapy.
Bye, now. No cops.
Something about this
just doesn't feel right.
Ah, donut and a fried egg.
You, stranger, are a man
of circular tastes.
On the subject of circles,
some associates of yours
roughed up a rotund gentleman
under my protection,
and now I am irate.
Hmm.
Did you ever hear the parable
of Lucifer and the millipede?
One day, a tiny millipede...
Get the hell out of my town,
or else!
Excuse me.
Have you seen this man?
Sure, that's the hobo
that eats the day,
olds out of our dumpster.
Haven't seen him today, though.
You just ate
your last cigar, old man.
Ah, coffee.
Exactly how I like it,
scalding hot!
Ah! But you said hot.
Hot!
Gun!
What the...
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Stayin'
You should've let me
finish my parable!
Ahoy‐hoy.
Huh?
Uh...
Why are you dipping
my face in dough?
Why are you kneading my face
into an "O" shape?
Why are you pushing my face
toward the deep fryer?
Oh, I see. Clever.
Madam.
Homer.
Oh, no.
Hands up. This is totally...
Oh, God! My God!
What the hell happened?!
Oh, Mafia guys! Headless dude!
Oh, Disco Man!
I need some water.
Oh! His face is a donut!
That is so messed‐up.
Captioning sponsored by
20th CENTURY FOX TELEVISION
FOX BROADCASTING COMPANY
And FORD.
We go further, so you can.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
Shh!