Mmm. When I die,
we should totally
get this sandwich place
for my memorial.
So good. Mmm. Can't wait.
Oh, all these people
loved Mr. Chase.
His students
are taking it so hard.
Yeah, nobody grieves
like theater kids.
This is my show!
Why are they singing
about computers?
- It was a musical about Y2
- K,
which was very scary back then.
Scarier than anything
we have now.
The whole show takes place
on New Year's Eve,
‐1999... ‐♪ Five, four, three
♪ Two, zero, zero, zero ♪
- ♪ A midnight countdown to Y2
- K ♪
♪ Five, four, three, two,
will I be a zero?
♪ When tomorrow becomes today. ♪
Mom, which one are you?
I was right over here.
In the wings,
calling all the shots...
as the stage manager.
Mrs. Chase,
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Oh, thank you, dear.
Say, look what I found
when I was cleaning out
Franklin's office.-
My prompt book.
This binder lists all the cues
for the entire production.
Oh, Franklin always said you
were the heart of the show‐‐
that your stage managing
was so... zealous.
I definitely ran a tight ship.
But in a fun way
everyone loved, obviously.
- Oh, yeah, totally.
- Super fun.
Of course, I would have loved
to have been in the show,
except I'm not much of a singer.
But in my imagination, I've got
the voice of a Disney princess.
Oh...
What a special time.
I'd give anything
to feel that magic again.
Script notes and sound cues
♪ Take me there again ♪
♪ In my blacks
in the backs of the wings
♪ So I'm not seen ♪
♪ No one knows the magic ♪
♪ That hides
behind the scenes
It's me!
The cast said yes!
We're putting on a musical!
Places, everybody
♪ It's time to start the show ♪
♪ That's what actors
need me to say
♪ Otherwise, they wouldn't
know where to go
♪ Cinch up the hemlines ♪
♪ Sound check all the mics ♪
♪ Close the door,
ring the bell
♪ And bring down
the house lights
♪ It's curtains up
for Marge Bouvier
♪ 'Cause I'm once again
the star
♪ Of the backstage ♪
Wow, you're the director?
No, more
important‐‐ the stage manager.
- Ah!
- Five minutes, guys!
- Thank you, five.
- Five minutes.
I always used to love
saying that, before...
The endless loads of laundry
♪ The dishes piled high ♪
♪ The whining and complaining ♪
‐♪ It's mine ♪ ‐♪ It's mine
- ♪ It's mine ♪
- Enough!
I'm returning to my
theater family
♪ A revival of
our fondest memories
‐♪ Singin'... ♪ ‐♪ Do
‐♪ Re ♪ ‐♪ Mi
- ♪ This ♪
‐♪ Show- ♪
♪ The talk of the town ♪
♪ A hit, a smash, the rage ♪
♪ And there's nothing
Springfield needs more
♪ Than a play ♪
Good!
'Cause I'm once again the
♪ Appreciated, well‐respected,
never, ever disconnected
♪ Nothing but
the most impressive
♪ Everybody's dearest friended ♪
♪ Star ♪
♪ Of the backstage... ♪
♪ She's the star,
see how she shines
♪ She answers
when we call for lines
♪ Places, everybody! ♪
Wow, honey,
those dorks are so excited to be
in your show again.
And I will do everything
I can to support you...
while I'm at Moe's.
Mwah.
Sorry, Marge, but I got to
drop out of the show.
I broke my hip
while singing and dancing
about feeling young again.
Say, Dad, what if
you filled in for Lenny
and joined Mom's musical?
Yeah, then you'd be the most
supportive husband ever.
Great idea, kids.
I'm all in, babe!
One pair of super tight
dance pants, please!
From this day forward,
we are enemies.
Forever and ever.
Forever.
Okay,
back on stage‐‐ it's just like
we're teenagers again.
Now let's start the rehearsal.
Theater!
Wait, we can't start
without Sasha Reed.
- She was the star of the show.
- Mm‐hmm.
She got into Julliard.
Sasha.
You never forget
your first diva.
I'd love to know
what she's been up to.
Well, as your dutiful
stage manager,
I did reach out repeatedly,
but never heard back.
I guess we'll never know
what happened
after Sasha
left little old Springfield
for New York City.
Never say never!
Hello, old friends!
Ah! It's Sasha!
Let me tell you all about it.
♪ It was a cold
and rainy morning
♪ When I exited the bus ♪
♪ I stepped into the city ♪
♪ Everyone in such a rush ♪
♪ I suppose I started singing ♪
♪ Just to keep
the chill at bay
♪ I guess I sounded
something like
♪ This ♪
♪ And that's when I heard
a man say
♪ "That tone, that pitch ♪
♪ "Your voice'll make us rich ♪
♪ Stick with me, and you'll
be destined to impress"
♪ And that's how Sasha became ♪
♪ A massive success ♪
♪ Yes, Sasha ♪
♪ Is a massive success ♪
♪ Now I dine on the veranda ♪
♪ With Lin‐Manuel Miranda ♪
♪ Scrape meat off the bone
with Patti LuPone
♪ Don't mention Glenn Close ♪
♪ I eat Bananas Foster ♪
♪ With my good friend
Sutton Foster
♪ Thanks to Stephen Sondheim,
who's the most gracious host
♪ Yes, I'm everything
you thought I'd be
♪ When I left Springfield
for the big city
♪ I've made it,
I'm a cut above the rest
♪ 'Cause Sasha has returned ♪
♪ A massive ♪
♪ Success... ♪
♪ That's right ♪
♪ I'm a Broadway ♪
♪ Star! ♪
Oh, I can't believe
Sasha came back.
What a career!
I know a famous person
that knows what's his name,
who is she,
and never heard of him!
Okay, okay, everybody.
It's so exciting that
Sasha is a massive success,
but we really need
to walk through our blocking.
Let's make it precise, gang!
Blocking, so important.
That's what Hal always told me.
Hal Prince.
Boom! Named it!
But before we get into
the technical stuff,
we need to reconnect
as an ensemblé.
Let's all go to my lake house
and do trust falls.
But we have to carve out
some time to run lines.
Marge Bouvier,
you have not changed a bit.
Okay, Mom, we'll run lines,
but don't wait up for us.
Us? What do you mean?
This bonding session
is for the cast.
You understand, right?
Oh.
Sure.
Of course.
Come on, friends!
I was wrong.
Theater kids are super cool.
Thanks for the hookup, honey.
♪ How will I stay alive? ♪
♪ When all ♪
♪ The computers think I died? ♪
‐♪ How will I ♪ ‐♪ How will I
♪ Stay alive ♪
♪ When all the clocks
and the computers
♪ Think I died? ♪
Okay, the curtain‐raiser
went a smidge long,
so stay on your marks next time.
- Take five!
- Thank you, five.
Anyway, I hope you all remember
the best part of rehearsal...
brownies!
Are those Margie's Brownies
with walnuts and M&Ms?
It's true, I do matter.
Look what else I'm included in.
It's all from our shows.
We were such a tight‐knit group.
Remember the tightness
of the knitting?
There's my old guitar pick.
Oh, I haven't played guitar
since I lost this!
Still works!
Oh, man, this takes me back...
Remember, guys?
♪ Bonfires at Billy's ♪
♪ We'd talk about our dreams ♪
♪ We'd get drunk
and make out, ha
♪ Cause a scene ♪
Remind me who Billy was again?
You know‐‐ Billy.
♪ Late nights at the diner ♪
♪ We'd laugh and we'd cry ♪
Right. Uh‐huh.
The diner.
♪ Smoking clove cigarettes ♪
♪ Ruthie serving us
cheese fries
Is that why you guys
always smelled
like burnt cinnamon?
♪ Climbing the water tower ♪
♪ Drunk on whiskey sours ♪
♪ Stealing the Lard Lad sign ♪
- That was you guys?
- Yeah.
♪ Remember the times ♪
♪ The best times ♪
♪ Of our lives ♪
♪ We had nothing but times ♪
♪ Remember the times ♪
Okay, I might've missed
some of those specific moments,
but I'm sure I'll remember
all the other ones.
What else?
♪ The kegger at Marge's ♪
♪ What an epic night ♪
Wait, there was a party
at my house?
Where was I?
♪ She was at
a tech run‐through
♪ Nowhere in sight ♪
Guys, that's like,
pretty messed up.
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ I was at that
super killer party, too
You weren't even in the show.
♪ Yeah, but I was cool ♪
♪ Lenny fell off the roof ♪
‐What? ‐♪ Marge's
parents got sued
♪ And had to file
for bankruptcy
Is that why I couldn't
go away to college?
♪ Remember the time ♪
♪ When Jackie died ♪
Wait, I thought Jackie moved.
♪ No one saw the signs ♪-
♪ Together we cried ♪
♪ And then we made it
about ourselves
♪ When the reporter came ♪
‐What?! ‐♪ He worked
for The Times ♪
Which one?
♪ The New York Times ♪
♪ Such timey times ♪
How'd I miss all of this?
♪ We were all together. ♪
Except me.
Script notes and sound cues
♪ They never saw me
as a friend
♪ In my blacks in the backs
of the wings
♪ I was unseen ♪
♪ So much for the magic ♪
♪ No one wants old Marjorie. ♪
I was unpopular and never knew!
All my best memories are ruined.
I wish I had never done
this stupid musical again.
As soon as Sasha showed up,
it was like I didn't exist.
I never liked that Sasha Reed.
Taking pop out of the fridge
without asking...
getting us sued...
Of course!
It's all Sasha's fault.
Someone ought to teach
that Broadway big shot a lesson.
Mom, do you
still have a computer?
Last night I made some
very interesting discoveries,
requiring the printing
of a revised playbill.
I'll refer you to page three
♪ To an updated biography ♪
♪ Of which you must see ♪
♪ Certain to change your view ♪
♪ Of the beloved ingenue ♪
♪ Sasha! Poof ♪
♪ The truth ♪
♪ She's never been in
a Broadway musical or play?
♪ She was never in Pippin,
Show Boat, or Cabaret? ♪
♪ She didn't sign autographs
at a stage door‐a?
♪ She worked at
the Herald Square Sephora?
♪ Lost hope, gave up
and moved the day
♪ She didn't get a
callback for Hairspray ♪
♪ She's a fraudway baby ♪
♪ A phony, a fake ♪
♪ She ain't got what it takes ♪
♪ She's a fraudway baby ♪
♪ She doesn't know
Sutton Foster
♪ This broad's an imposter ♪
♪ She's had you wrapped
around her finger
♪ For days ♪
♪ But she's nothing
but a hair‐extentioned
♪ Makeup‐slinging,
Botox‐forehead
♪ Lying, cheating ♪
♪ Baby fraudway... ♪
So you don't know the people
you said you knew
but who are they?
Marge Bouvier, you're...
mean!
Well, I'm sure you're all
as angry at Sasha as I am,
but now we can wipe
the slate clean
and really come together
as a theater family.
Without Sasha, there's no show.
You ruined everything,
you... techie!
But, w‐w‐wait.
She made it all up.
She's a liar!
I think this is
the kind of thing
that makes people not want
to invite you to stuff.
Stupid, ungrateful cast.
Did you sleep at all last night?
"We don't care
that Sasha's a liar."
"We still love her
more than you."
Mo‐om!
Bart replaced my Kashi cereal
with woodchips
from the hamster cage!
So? You didn't notice
till I told you.
‐
- What's wrong with Mom?
- Well, kids, your mother has
severely pissed off
all the theater weirdos‐‐
of which I am now one‐‐
but she can't see
it's her fault.
So... are you gonna tell her?
Indeed I am, and there's
only one way to do it.
♪ When your partner's
in a tizzy
♪ Flossing till she's dizzy ♪
♪ Clearly in the wrong,
but certain she's right
♪ It's your responsibility ♪
♪ To imply her culpability ♪
♪ In a way that doesn't
instigate a fight
‐ ‐Whoops.
♪ Don't escalate the situation ♪
♪ Or add further complication ♪
♪ Mince your words,
so as never to encroach
♪ Deliver your advice ♪
♪ But make sure to do it nice ♪
♪ For it's best to use
a delicate approach
Marge, darling...
Leave me alone!
Marge, listen!
I'm being delicate!
Oh, are you?
♪ Now, I know you may think
you were just in your actions
♪ But it makes my heart sink
to see your infractions
♪ Your feelings were hurt,
but it's malice you blurt
♪ Your transaction
compels a retraction
Oh, you're right, Homie.
It's all my fault.
I did the one thing
I put myself before the show.
You see, kids?
♪ It's best to use a delicate ♪
♪ Approach. ♪
I have to make things right.
You need to let me see
the cast‐only text chain.
Yeah, I don't know.
It's really not cool
for me to share it.
Plus, you wouldn't get
any of the jokes.
You might want
to skip over the stuff
with your name in it.
Sasha hasn't left town.
There's still time.
Why would Marge do that to me?
I was never mean to her.
I never even talked to her!
Yeah, we don't care
that you only sell makeup
and that you're a huge liar.
I miss high school.
Remember the night
of the cast party?
You and me... in the hot tub?
That night really happened?
I thought I imagined it.
It was real.
And I've never had better.
Ah...
Sasha!
Sasha, I'm so sorry.
Once my husband
sang and danced to me
about what I did,
I felt terrible.
I acted like
such a crazy teenager.
All I wanted to do was
recapture my glory days,
when I could've
become anything...
instead of what I really am,
a floor manager at Sephora.
Sales associate.
I guess we both wanted
to be stars again.
There she is.
Probably called us here
to expose the lies
the rest of us put
in our playbill bios.
What lies?
I am
"thrilled to reprise my role
- as Steve/
- Ensemble."
I was supposed
to manage the stage,
but instead I just managed
to screw everything up.
But there's still time
to put on the best show
of the latter part of our lives.
What do you say?
Should we give it a try?
Oh, why should we?
What has trying
ever gotten anyone?
♪ I could've been a crooner ♪
♪ Star of stage and screen ♪
♪ But I'd just as sooner ♪
♪ Drink away my dream ♪
- ♪ Never try. ♪
- Stop!
That's the saddest thing
I've ever heard.
Barney, nobody needs
to do this show more than you.
♪ Except me! ♪
‐ ‐Yay!
It's a full house, so...
♪ Places, everybody. ♪
Marge, when I'm onstage
and it's not my turn to talk,
- can I look at my phone?
- No.
It's almost midnight.
What's going to happen?
Oops.
Five, four...
Three, two, one!
‐ ‐So the show just ends?
What a cop‐out!
At least at the endof Rent
you get to see
Mimi come back to life.
This is just lazy.
♪ ♪-
Marge, thanks for reminding me
how good it feels
to be a big fish
in a small pond.
I guess that's why
you never left.
Actually, I think
it was because my parents
couldn't afford college
after a lawsuit from a party
you threw at my house
but didn't invite me to.
Such timey times.
Oh, my God, it's really her.
It's Marge Bouvier.
Just ask her.
Um, would you please
sign my prompt bible?
You know me?
You're a stage‐managing icon!
Would you go
to the diner with us?
We'd die to hear
some of your stories.
Invited to the diner.
I'm getting cheese fries!
Cast party at Marge's house!
‐ ‐All right!
Theater!
- Y2 - K ♪ Five, four,
three, two, zero, zero, zero
♪ A new millennium ♪
♪ But who will I be? ♪
♪ Five, four, three, two ♪
♪ Way too many zeros ♪
♪ What will the computers ♪
♪ Do to me? ♪
♪ Will there be blackouts? ♪
♪ Chaos? ♪
♪ Motherboards exploding? ♪
♪ Glitches and crashes? ♪
♪ A run on the banks? ♪
♪ Will I have a mortgage? ♪
♪ A family?
A boy and a girl?
♪ What happens
to a two‐digit soul
♪ In a four‐digit world? ♪
Shh!