♪ Love is a song
that never ends ♪
♪ Sunshine turns to rain ♪
♪ In Disney cartoons,
a parent dies ♪
♪ Life will be full of pain ♪
♪ We bring tears
to children's eyes ♪
♪ They'll never sleep again ♪
♪ Ooh. ♪
Barti, wait for me.
Shh!
Stop all that noise.
A hunter has entered the forest.
Cool.
What's a hunter?
- Run, Barti, run!
- Not without you, Mama.
Owl season starts next week.
Next week!
‐ ‐Death.
Barti, if you love me, run!
I made it, Mama.
Mama?
Mama?!
Where‐where's my mama?
I'm fine, sweetheart.
I'm fine.
Your father took care of
the bad man.
Time for a little "stag party."
- Thank God you're herbivores.
- That's right.
And today your name is "Herb."
This family is so poor.
I hate to say it,
but you are a bad provider.
Hey, I put
a roof over your head.
Okay, under your head.
Family, I have excellent news.
I got a job as a tutor
in a nice, rich home.
How deep is the water
in their living room?
There's no water
in their living room.
That's a thing?
Oh, Homie, use a coaster.
Okay, here's a math problem.
How long can the two of us
watch your hundred‐inch TV
before anyone gets wise?
"Y" equals 102.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I want to watch TV.
Tickets.
Oh, blood and guts.
Sir, you're not happy
with me? Why?
You have the poor person smell.
Gas station ramen,
a whiff of despair.
May I?
Oh, also class resentment.
Almost boiling over.
- Very dangerous.
- Mm‐hmm.
Now leave. I just have
to find another idiot
to take your job.
Idiot, eh?
How did you
hear about this position?
Well, through proper channels.
Certainly not through
your tutor,
who I never met,
Or your new maid, Marge.
Or your‐‐
Lisa, what's your job again?
Uh, sir, I'm the art teacher.
Aw, you've loved art ever
since you were a little...
late for the job interview.
Ja, ja. Gut.
We are leaving
on a long vacation.
Here are the keys to the beer
garden, the saxophone room,
and my armory of stink bombs.
- Can we trust you?
- Honored sir,
we are beyond reproach.
Especially the new groundskeeper.
Ah.
I think she has
a thing for the pool boy.
Stupid rich people.
While they're gone, we eat
their food, drink their booze,
and break
their complicated toilets.
I was not built
for the American ass.
He thinks
I am a drinking fountain. Ugh.
Who could that be?
At this hour?
In the pouring rain?
Please let me in.
My jeans are wet.
And they're
my only pair of pants.
Oh, you poor, poor man.
Can I get you some tea?
Oh, yeah, I‐I know where it is.
Sir, what are you doing?
I need to go...
downstairs.
Daddy's coming!
Go on... without me.
Really, fatso?
You're that exhausted
going downstairs?
Why, you little...
Huh?
That's right, I hid my family
in this cramped,
windowless basement.
This is nicer than our house.
See what I mean?
Bad provider.
Everything was great
until you parasites
took our jobs.
You're squatting in the basement
and you're calling us parasites?
Well, maybe the truth is
the master is the parasite
because he exploits us all,
and, um, yeah, okay.
This is where you're supposed
to be smacking them
- with the frying pan.
- Sorry.
- Parasites.
- Parasites!
Geez, how many people
live down here?
People of all incomes.
This house is an allegory.
Emphasis on "gory."
You don't have
a worthwhile bone in your body.
Wait! If we all work together,
regardless of class,
we could finally change
everything for the better.
Wow, that sounds great.
Unless it's socialism.
Not totally,
but certain aspects are
- similar to social...
- Kill her!
Seeing all that horror
and poverty makes me think
- we should lower the corporate
tax rate even further. - Agreed.
There's no way they
can get up here, is there?
Heh, heh, heh.
My last words are
"I'm too young
and beautiful to die.
Take a baby instead."
Well, Marge, I finally
got you a house with no leaks.
Yeah, but it's filled
with dead bodies.
Some people are never happy.
And they say on moonless nights,
just like this one,
in ordinary neighborhoods,
the ghost of
the murdered squirrel
leaps, treehouse to treehouse,
biting the toes of little girls.
You sure scared them.
- Can you get off my lap?
- In due time.
Oh, Marge.
I did a chore today.
Which one?
Unloaded the dishwasher.
All... the... way.
Ooh.
Mom, Dad,
can we sleep in your bed?
Oh, which scary story did
Bart tell you this time?
The one where the little girl's
head is filled with potato bugs,
and there's no way she can tell?
'Cause that's
only partially true.
No! And that's even worse!
Lousy treehouse.
Every year,
two of them good,
and a lame one in the middle.
I'll put an end to that.
Stupid hard work.
Who dares cleave my trunk,
because...
You keep talkin'.
I'm gonna chop you down
before you finish that sentence.
I am Groot.
Hmm. You're real mature.
Laughin' at
a brain‐damaged tree.
Help! Help! S‐O‐S!
Is there a dendrologist
in the house?
And this is
the Doppler Effect...
Always teaching science...
Oh, ain't that nice?
A tree farm.
No!
This holiday is worse
than Dutch Elm Disease.
Eh, no offense there.
Oh, yeah...
Humans have abused us
for too long.
Today we celebrate
our Arbor Day.
We have got to get
a better name for that holiday.
I may live in the human world,
but I never forget
my tree roots.
Hey! How'd you like me
to pick something off you?
I didn't like it at all.
Feed me. Feed me!
You're not a tree.
You're a plant.
Yes, but I identify as a tree.
I'm a trans‐plant.
A legion of forest grumps
is heading into town,
bent on revenge for years of
bad tree‐tment.
This just in, my chest...
All right, this is it.
No tree is a match for
a human with a wooden bat.
First, we kill them,
then we hang our hammocks!
(cheering
Finally I'll get my revenge
for all the leaves I had
to rake, and all the prunin'.
And the times a tree leaped
out in front of me tractor
when I was textin' me friends.
Gah!
Oh, no. Pollen!
And I'm all
out of antihistamine.
Huh?
Time to hit me a homer.
Whee!
Oh, the trees won.
Another crass play for
an environmental award.
You will make
a fine beanbag chair.
That is very difficult
to dispute.
However...
Oh, boy...
Halloween isn't over,
and they're already
starting with Christmas.
In January, Bart was awful,
put earthworms
in his father's waffle.
In February, the dead of winter,
Bart catfished teacher,
right on Tinder.
In March,
we saw the start of spring.
Bart unscrewed
the playground swing.
April's known for paying taxes.
For Bart, it's known
for nude butt faxes.
- In May...
- Oh, how many months are there?!
In May we dance around a pole.
Bart knocked it down
with a car he stole.
June is halfway through
the year.
Bart has a sip
of his first beer.
July is when the Bastille falls.
Bart cuts heads
off Lisa's dolls.
August is always a scorcher.
Bart perfects
his turtle torture.
September,
Bart won't even mention.
He spends the whole month
in detention.
October ends with Halloween.
Bart eats candy till he's green.
In November,
Bart can carve the turkey.
He'll be serving human jerky.
Then, worst of all,
in cold December...
R. I. P.
Lisa, we have
something to tell you.
We had a party
and didn't invite you.
It was a week ago.
We watched a cool TikTok.
But anyone
who watches the TikTok
dies after seven days.
I watched it first.
Oopsie!
Finally, I'm not a twin anymore.
I can have the top bunk and...
I killed Jerry and Larry.
Bart, have you heard
about this deadly TikTok?
Oh, yeah. Everyone was invited
to that party except you.
- Even Milhouse?
- I was the bouncer.
Then I watched that
TikTok eight times.
I didn't watch it.
But you can if you want.
Nice try.
If we knew
what was in that video,
maybe we could stop it.
We just have to find someone
who isn't afraid of death
and likes to watch TV.
I'm your man.
But, Grampa, if you do watch,
you die in seven days.
That's three more
than the doctor gave me.
Okay.
First,
there's an evil‐looking ring.
Then an empty chair.
Then a lady combing her hair.
I like the old movies
where the combing was implied.
Now there's a bunch of maggots.
Satan head.
More maggots. More maggots.
No, wait,
that's an ad for Chipotle.
Now a woman's jumping
off a cliff,
and we end up
with an abandoned well.
This is the kind of movie
you watch in a museum
when your feet hurt.
And my feet always hurt.
Seven days.
What?
I can't hear ya.
Seven days.
Maybe I better jot this down.
What was your name again?
I don't know who you are
or what you want,
but let me give you
my credit card number.
I don't have time
for your nonsense.
We have bigger problems.
Steroid allegations
on the kickball team.
Psst.
I know about
your infernal TikTok.
This is the tragic tale
of a sad second‐grader.
Mopey Mary, they called her.
Kids can be so cruel.
Ooh, "Mopey." The worst thing
you can call someone in 1932.
One cold February,
after receiving naught
in her Valentine's box
but a poop
from the class rabbit,
poor Mary ran
to the old school well
and threw herself in.
She was down there
for seven days
before anyone bothered to look.
Fortunately,
it was the end of my shift.
Wait a minute.
We don't have a school well.
I covered it
so no one would
ever go near it again.
They say the unhappy spirit
of Mopey Mary lurks
in the murderous video
shared by popular children.
Shouldn't you have
told the police first?
I tried to tell Wiggum.
He got scared and ran off.
Daddy, that's my pee‐pee bed.
Uh, not anymore.
Looks like it's up to me
to save the school.
I can do this.
Beware.
Milhouse?
Yeah. It was really nice of
them to give me ghost glasses.
Now, be careful, Lisa.
And can you kill off
a Hershey bar for me?
I think that's how I get one.
The rules aren't very clear
up here.
I will.
Seven days.
- Coward!
- Say what?
I don't want to wait seven days.
So... come and get me now.
Uh, I have to move
some stuff around; just a sec.
Killing you is very
important to us. Please hold.
Your curse will be answered
in the order it was received.
Okay, um, how's Wednesday?
I've got a guy coming to look at
the air conditioner
in the morning.
Kill me now or kill me never.
Fine!
Hello, Mary.
I'm not scared.
Um, would you mind taking those
black boots off in the house?
Oh, wait.
Those are your feet!
Um, I wanted to give you
something.
Something that will change
the way you look at the world.
Here it is.
A valentine? For me?
I want to be your friend.
I want to braid your hair
and see your beautiful face.
Ah! All right. All right.
We'll work with that. Oh...
You know why I'm smiling?
‐ ‐'Cause I have a best friend!
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Best friend?
I've already suffocated.
Give me a little space.
Okay, no problem.
Hey, I wrote you
a song on the saxophone.
It's called "Well Bottom Blues."
I'll tell you what.
I'm just gonna walk
right over here, okay?
You sound great.
I bet it sounds even better
from the bottom of the well.
♪ We'll see you next Halloween ♪
♪ With tales of horror
and pain ♪
♪ Treehouse X‐X‐X‐I‐I‐I ♪
♪ Take a trip down
Dismembering Lane ♪
♪ Where were Kang
and Kodos this time? ♪
♪ Crammed into
the final frame. ♪
We're dimmer stars
than Proxima Centauri.
Let's go drown our sorrows
in a child's blood.
Hasn't there been enough death
in this episode?
Really?