Don't rot your brain
on Satan's calculator.
Babies need real toys
like these.
- It's Princess Maggie.
Princess Maggie's here.
Princess Maggie, what's wrong?
The girl is bored.
Royal court,
entertain my daughter at once.
No princess can frown
when her eardrums are pulsing
with the beat
of iambic pentameter.
That's quite a frown.
Out of my way!
I've got no shame
or regard for my own well-being.
Hey, hey!
You fools have failed
the princess.
We have no other option.
We must give her...
- the special gift.
Goodbye, Princess Maggie.
Goodbye.
¡Ay, caramba!
Oh, boy.
Homer,
your father's
messing up the baby again.
Way ahead of you, pal.
My eyes...
Where did all this traffic
come from?
It's like my favorite
movie ever, Cars 3.
I hated Cars 1 and 2.
I'm unsupervised.
Have no fear.
Safety is here.
Traffic, no traffic...
What's the difference?
I got nothing to be late for
and no one who cares.
Let's take this from Disney+
to HBO Max.
Oh, Marge, you haven't honked
like this since high school.
It's a traffic jam.
My, my, look at all those middle
fingers raised to the Lord.
Wait a minute.
That car looks familiar.
Hey, that looks like...
No, don't go there, Moe.
Don't go there.
Erase, erase, erase!
Oh, come on.
We put up a sign and everything.
This is so unreal.
Why did all this traffic
suddenly appear on our street?
Wayz told me this was
the fastest route.
That's important when
you're selling your organs.
Oh, my God, I've heard of this.
That app routes traffic
through a quiet
residential neighborhood,
turning it into
a gridlocked nightmare.
Sorry, I met someone
in another car.
We need to do something.
This is driving
the neighborhood nuts.
Even the guy who's always
in his underwear.
This is more
than I put on for Zoom.
Enough with the traffic.
I'm calling
a neighborhood meeting.
Neighborhood Meeting.
Neighborhood meeting.
Please rate my app.
Two stars? My IPO is ruined.
Ruined! Ruined!
We're here to talk about
the terrible problem
on our street.
- Finally.
- About time.
We assume you're talking
about you, the Simpsons.
Wha...?
I've seen the boy's moons
more times
than I've seen the real one,
and I'm an astronomer.
What's wrong with us?
You haven't stopped by
to say hello in 25 years,
and I live next door.
The only good one's the baby,
and she shot a guy.
Wait, are we ignoring
the elephant in the room?
By which I mean
the big, fat husband.
Every time Homer
wears corduroys,
I just hear those thighs
scraping, scraping, scraping.
Oh, my God.
I'm starting to get the idea
you think
we're not good neighbors.
You see? You see?
Now, don't worry, my friends.
I'm stepping forward
to fix this traffic.
And by doing so, maybe...
just maybe I'll fix
my reputation with you all.
So just say to me what I say
to Tinker "I believe."
And... off I go.
Um... no.
"Identify all traffic lights."
Done.
"Identify all yield signs."
"Identify all the crosswalks."
Oh! Lisa, help me.
Done.
"Identify all fire hydrants."
Jesuits? Done.
20th-century dictators?
Uh, overrated fiction?
Hyperintelligent
cartoon characters?
Vegan nut milks?
Future criminals?
Aah! New England doorways!
Oh, forget this.
I'm calling instead.
You've reached
Wayz customer service.
You have 5,700 callers
ahead of you.
Now, please enjoy the frustrated
noises of other callers on hold.
I'm gonna blow my brains out.
- You again?
Can it be her,
after all these years?
The woman I thought was the one
stuck behind my car?
Hi, Moe. I missed you.
I never should've left.
Maya. The longest,
best relationship of my life.
That was a great six days.
You're a good kisser.
Yeah.
I practice by siphoning gas
out of other people's tanks.
So, is there a knob or an
"open sesame" type deal or what?
My house is over there.
Wha...?
Every day since you left me,
I've written you a letter.
Really wish I had gotten
your address.
So, how you been, Maya?
Well, I finally got my PhD.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
You taking medicine
for that or what?
Oh, Moe.
It's nice to laugh again.
How are you?
Oh, I-I'm doing great.
Yeah, the factory closed,
so there's lots of new drunks.
And, uh, oh, the bathroom possum
is getting real good
at handing out them combs.
Who am I kidding?
My life is a wreck, Maya.
The face recognition software
on my phone says, "Yuck."
My playlist only has
breakup songs.
It's rough,
I'm telling you, yeah.
I miss you, Moses Marie Szyslak.
Oh, no, no, no.
Please don't give me that look.
I can't go through it
again, Maya. I can't.
Ah, just look at you walking
toward me, coming closer,
with those big green eyes
of yours
and the great-smelling hair,
skin smoother
than American cheese.
But I want a drink now.
Oh, I wish this moment could
last forever, like, uh...
uh, I don't know, uh,
Henry Winkler's career.
Boy, that guy
never jumped the shark.
Not even when
he jumped the shark.
Just so I know, have you had
another girlfriend since me?
Uh, not really, no.
Uh, no one could match you.
I mean, I have been
catfished a few times.
Hey, Moe.
It's us, "Online Gloria."
I'll kill you!
Also, I love you.
Oh, Moe, you poor guy.
Oh, everything is perfect.
Which it always is
until I say, "I love you."
I love you.
I love you. Will you marry me?
To hell with women.
I love you, New York.
Help me. Spider-Man!
Professor, can you get
the traffic off our street?
I'll give you anything
except for money
or credit for what you did.
The only way to defeat
a global data behemoth
is to get into the source code.
Just look what I did here
on, uh... on the Wikipedia.
Welcome to Wayz.
We figure out the fastest route
to get you where you want to go.
Our secret?
Always collecting data.
But we would never misuse it.
Who do you think we are, Google?
We're owned by Google.
I've got the answer.
What if we made your street...
not exist?
Well, where would we live?
Well, that's quite silly.
It would, of course,
still exist in real life,
but I could make it disappear
from the database.
- All right, let us see here.
Uh, keystrokes, keystrokes,
escape key,
both colon and semicolon,
backslash, backslash,
ampersand...
we come to a new day
on "no such street."
Never again
will we be afraid of cars.
Get thee out of my way, English!
It's time to play
in the streets!
Haw-haw!
Climate change is real.
They know I did this.
They're making eye contact
with me. Eye contact.
Even the guy
with the boat in his driveway.
Hey, hey, Homer, want to come
on my boat with me?
In the water?
Eh, we'll see.
Uh, one step at a time.
I will never get tired of this.
Never. Never, ever.
So, what do you feel like doing?
I don't know, I...
I feel like singing.
Hey, are you guys an item again?
Well, maybe, maybe.
We definitely are.
He has a toothbrush at my place.
Yeah, but, yeah, it's a rental.
Moe's the best thing
that's ever happened to me.
And this time, it's gonna last.
Way to go, Moe. Three cheers.
Hip, hip, hooray!
Hip, hip, hooray! Hip, hip...
Homer, come in
the alley with me.
My doctor warned me not
to cut off a "hip, hip, hooray."
Look, Maya left me once.
I just know she's gonna
leave me again.
This-this is a disaster.
You're the only guy here who
knows how to hold on to a woman.
What is your secret?
How do you keep Midge?
Well, it's, uh... it's, um...
Hmm.
It helps
if you get them pregnant.
Please, I need some actual,
real advice here.
Yeah, I better call Midge.
Hello.
Honey, I'm here in the alley
with Moe.
The only woman
who ever loved him came back,
and he's afraid
she's gonna leave him again.
What should he do?
Hand him the phone.
Moe, trust love.
Gotcha.
Your wife's an idiot.
Another tray of doughnuts.
This time from
that family over there.
Geez, I can't take
all this adulation.
This must be what drove
Randy Quaid crazy.
Mr. Simpson, will you throw out
the first pitch
at my Little League game?
Want to have coffee
on my boat in the parking lot?
Do you ever take it
in the water?
Not yet.
Please, I'm just here to eat.
Geez, you were mad
they didn't like you,
and now you're mad
they like you.
I just want to be left alone
with my to-do list.
Excuse me.
Will you be godfather
to my baby?
Let me see it.
Ugh. Pass.
Okay, Moe.
I'll be back in 20 minutes.
I'm just getting
some stuff for dinner.
- Love you.
- Mwah.
Love you, too.
Moe. Oh, Moe.
Huh?
Look at you. Look at us.
She's not gonna come back.
- They never come back.
- Oh, yeah?
Well, this time,
I'm not gonna listen to mirrors
or mud puddles
or my upside-down face
in a spoon.
This time, I'm gonna believe.
Oh, no, you're not.
No one could love you.
Stop it, stop it, stop it!
What does it take
to get a beer around here?
Shut up!
Shut up?
I would stop coming here
if you weren't the only place
in stumbling distance.
You are not real.
You're just that nagging
voice of self-doubt
that lives in my head.
That's right.
Easy in, easy out.
Well, this time,
I'm gonna stop you
before you wreck my life.
Now you're a loser
with seven years bad luck.
I guess what
we're trying to say is...
You're right.
You beautiful bastards
are right.
- Mm-hmm.
- Ah, yeah.
Huh? What the...?
Moe? You're hiding here?
Yeah. Bart's treehouse
is the one place
no one will look for me.
Plus, there are
no girls allowed,
which, uh, helps.
Moe's going through
a tough time, son.
Just play around him.
We'll just pretend
he's a dead, rotting alien.
Thank you, son.
The alien's alive!
- And it has feelings.
- Kill him!
I'm sorry, no breakfast
until you get Moe out
of the treehouse.
And I'll keep your bacon safe
while you're gone.
Thank God I have
my pocket bacon.
Moe, you can't stay here
anymore.
Sure, I can. Uh, you want
some eggs with that?
I got 'em out of that nest
over there.
Just one.
I don't want to be rude.
Listen, Moe,
every once in a while,
a beautiful woman falls in love
with a homely guy like us.
You got to make the most of it.
If Kevin James can find
happiness, why can't you?
And he was always
wearing shorts.
You know, after all these years,
I dated all these women,
and it always just goes back
to square one.
Lonely old Moe.
Well, there is
a way around that.
You could propose.
Wha...?
What are you proposing
I propose?
I mean the big "M."
- Murder-suicide?
- No.
- Marriage.
- Marriage? Whoa.
You mean I could have
the thing you're always
coming into my bar
and moaning about?
You know what? She's worth it.
I'll give it a shot.
Okay. This is as far as we go.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
Let me just
straighten myself up.
You'd better speak fast,
or for the second time,
you're gonna lose
the first good thing
that's ever happened to you.
I'm so sorry.
You're great, so great,
and all I've been is afraid.
But all I got to do
is look in your eyes.
Baby, I love you so much.
You stick with me, you'll get
everything you ever wanted.
I will never doubt you again.
You can control the remote.
You can pick all our vacations.
And because I know
the ladies like it this way,
I will leave the toilet seat on.
Maya, will you marry me?
Forget it, loser.
Gorillas like us
don't get the girl.
We're lucky if our cage
gets hosed down once a week.
Yes.
I knew it! That's it.
I'm never getting up again.
Staying here, on the ground.
Wait, you-you said yes.
Yes, Moe. Yes.
Good song, but, uh,
the movie is crap.
What is it, Mosie?
Oh, it's just, uh...
I ain't never been able
to use this...
until now.
- Aw.
Here you go, my good man.
Eh, this expired-a
ten years ago.
Ah, damn it!
FOX BROADCASTING COMPANY
And FORD.
We go further, so you can.
"Identify all
the existentialists."
Celebrity chefs.
Very soft minerals.
Bebop jazz musicians. Yes!
Tropical birds.
Chess grand masters?
Stone fruits?
American Revolutionary battles?
Nail shank diameters?
Aah! And I'm in. Ha.
Lisa, time for bed.
Oh, man.
Shh!