Hey, bunch of noses!
Whoa...
Who are you?
No.
I'm Lt. Castel.
Yeah?
- Yes.
Chair.
Captain.
A small, strong black coffee.
- With pleasure.
CLEAR DARKNESS
Yeah, how are you?
Aren't you coming today?
OK.
...their cries in the slaughterhouse!
- Drop it.
We kill 2 billion animals weekly.
Forget your plan.
You don't want to help me anymore.
We'll talk about it tomorrow.
Hey Maude.
- Eat a little?
Since when?
- It's a time to talk
if you have the opportunity.
How are you doing in high school?
How are YOU doing?
You talk to your father, talk
to me too.
You're not my mother, I'm doing well,
don't force it.
Thanks for the coffee.
♪ Don't look yet, the shadow of a will ♪
Please, stop-
♪ Our love isn't dead ♪
♪ He sleeps outrageously ♪
♪ Somewhere in the azure, the
extravagant void ♪
♪ Our love measures infinitely large ♪
♪ But finally, tell me
What does it prove? ♪
♪ It's stupid as a star
When the night comes to light ♪
Look there!
A pack?
We say 'horde' or 'herd.'
They swarm.
- Is it due to the climate warming?
The absence of predators.
- Exactly.
We have to find a balance between
control and proliferation,
and protect them.
Did you see the time?
You want to go home?
- My parents will flip their lids.
You'll protect me, like the animals.
I'll catch up with you.
OK.
Are you following me?
- No, I'm walking.
Stay with us.
You shouldn't have quit.
Hi.
- Hi.
Come back.
- I don't know.
We miss you.
Hey!
- I'm coming.
It's not too late?
- You finished the year.
Yes.
- Yes.
Good morning, Colonel.
- Mr. Mayor, Prefect.
Fuck. All good?
Good morning.
- We're about to decorate you,
The General of the Army is there,
and you arrive in this get-up.
Seriously, Captain.
- It's clean...
Go and change. Now.
She made a face at me.
The recipient of-
I don't care!
About anything!
Ugly!
A call, who's calling me?
Yeah?
; fuck.
Very well, I'm coming.
We're waiting for you.
No time, an emergency.
Gotta go, Happy New Year!
So, cause of death?
- A blow to the temple.
With bare hands?
It was no Mike Tyson. I opt
for a bladed weapon.
Time of death?
Between 10 pm and midnight.
No signs of a struggle?
- No.
Not easy.
Wow, elegant!
- I'm good!
It won't be easy.
- Why?
Claire Duret,
- Yeah...
17, by the ID found on her.
It was a jogger who called;
says he's been waiting and
wants to finish his run.
He'll wait. Where is she?
- Down there.
Thanks, honey.
Oscar! How are you, my homey?
Captain.
- Covid kiss.
Nice to see you.
How goes it with you?
Well; poor kid.
Where's the asshole?
- Down there.
Thanks, I can manage.
So, in a hurry?
- I said all I have to say.
Less than the kid.
Didn't that affect you?
Yes, but-
- Tell me.
I wanted to see my stats: calories
burned, gradient.
What a Big Ben! 90 calories per hour.
You saw?
- I saw her hand sticking out,
as I was passing.
Poor girl. That's all?
We'll ask around.
Did you get his name?
- Yes.
And get his DNA?
- No.
My DNA?
To see if you hit her. We have
to search you.
You can't.
- Yes.
I'm going.
- No, hey hey! Come here.
Empty your pockets. Go on!
No, but-
- There's that.
As if by chance.
Where was this?
Next to her.
- Next to her where?
There are numbers, which number?
Number 4.
- You're sure?
Not next to that?
Killing for that is stupid.
- No.
We'll, maybe. Good.
Christophe, Richard. Take him away.
We'll talk by the fire.
Huh? Seriously?
- Well yes!
No.
- Yes.
Come ON!
- You'll like the chicken, it's good.
Wait, I want to check something.
Take her arm.
So; hey...
Do we agree, it's too big.
Yes.
- No sign of dragging.
She was killed here.
- Impossible,
not according to the lividity
of her skin.
Was she carried here?
Yes, but you have to be strong.
Yes, or: there was more than one.
Wait, she'll call.
She wouldn't leave without saying.
- And if she's not at Jules's?
Good morning.
Gendarmerie, Captain Marleau.
Claire Duret is your daughter?
Indeed.
- My step-daughter.
We found your daughter's body
this morning.
Claire?
It's not true.
Did she suffer?
- No,
the first blow was fatal.
On her here, a focal contusion to
the cerebellum.
Immediate brain disconnect.
She didn't feel anything.
After her mother's death 10 years ago,
we continued to treat her as living.
Can you leave us, please?
My husband came home this
morning from a seminar.
And you?
I was at a party for parents of students.
Her high school?
- Yes, I'm the principal.
Principal and stepmother, you're
cumulative.
Yeah, by the way,
do you know this?
I had just offered it to her,
to bring us closer.
It was my grandmother's.
- It's too big.
It had to be adjusted, but I imagine
she'd still wear it.
Excuse me, I must leave you.
Please, madam.
Are you there?
The jogger was telling the truth,
he's clean.
We let him go.
- Not immediately.
It's not time for his run.
Happy Happy
New Year! New Year!
How Good
are you? morning!
He's strange.
I'm not going to beat around the
bush, we've received sad news.
Claire was found dead this morning.
Well?
Pythagoras' theorem.
It's not funny, she's dead.
I'm looking for her cell phone; because
she didn't have it.
Nice photo.
Who is it?
Her boyfriend, Jules Tivner.
Super.
That poster.
It's about changing the environment.
A nice kid.
What was her trip: wildlife, climate?
She had a webpage denouncing
polluters and hunters.
She got threats.
- Yeah? What kind?
"watch out for hunting accidents."
Did you report them?
A complaint, but there was
no follow-up.
What did you find?
- Nothing.
Shit. Her password, do you have it?
Date of birth?
- No, that never works.
You always spoil the fun.
What's her date of birth?
May 5, 2004.
"May 5, 2004."
Tap-tap.
It doesn't work.
What's that?
It's for you.
My birthday is soon.
- Happy birthday.
What is it?
- A mute;
I play the trumpet.
I'm starting out, and I was scared
of disturbing her when she
was studying.
Thank you.
The neighbor at #36 offered to help.
Madam Principal.
How are you?
Your opinion of Mr. Murat?
Yannick Murat?
Your stepdaughter's homeroom teacher.
That's his name, Murat?
- What did you say?
What'd he say? He just said:
"One day my daughter started to
skip Mr. Murat's classes
and changed her major." Why,
Madam Principal?
She liked many subjects.
When so close to a degree?
I'll bring the coffees.
She wanted to change majors, or
change teachers?
He didn't kill her.
They threatened her.
Yes, we'll look at that.
Look into it, will you?
Someone broke a windowpane in the
middle of the night.
It's linked.
It has to be linked, yeah? Yeah.
Where can we see Mr. Murat?
ELECTIONS, NOT WORDS
NO TO THE AGRICULTURE
SCHOOL EXPANSION
"No to the high
school expansion."
Neither god nor mistress!
That's cool. Who lives there?
Rufus? He's just a complainer.
Yeah?
DU MONCEAU AGRICULTURAL
HIGH SCHOOL OF BLOIS
Where are his students?
You can expect anything with him.
- Everything?
He has his style, his method.
He's holding class outside.
- OK.
Normally, a lecture
is masterfully boring.
The day before yesterday they
slept in the forest.
The state forest, over there?
For some parents, it opens the
door to abuses.
But we need teachers like him
who encourage independence and
strong friendships.
It takes everything.
It's the forest where we found
your step-daughter.
What are you doing?
- Well, I'm digging.
"Are your friends green?"
"Will it go green?"
Your life goes on, but
but without forgetting Claire's memory.
It's like this mimosa:
perennial, vital.
Who could have killed her?
If they come back, I'm here.
It's too late.
- No, Jules.
Would Claire want us to forget
about her murderer?
Let justice be done.
- It's warm.
Good morning all.
We're creating a support group.
No need.
Maybe not you, but your friends-
He's right, we have Yannick.
Who's Jules?
- That's me.
Can we talk?
- Don't harass him.
"Justice," your word.
Let's talk about harassment, Professor-?
Murat.
Come.
Come on; I'm not gonna eat you.
You're wrong, she was just
a friend.
Yeah?
- Yeah.
What do you want?
- Her phone.
It's not here.
- No?
Welcome to my home.
That's it.
And not her phone?
- No...
Your desk?
- Yes.
Well then!
There you both are.
And a boyfriend?
Where were you last night?
- In bed, ask my roommates.
If we go out, we write it down.
The rules!
I know, I would sneak out too.
How come your girlfriend left
Murat's class?
She said nothing to me.
- Diony.
She hadn't spoken to you
about Murat: your good master,
your "precious"?
Our "guru"? You all say that.
Is that so?
And who says that?
He treats us all like adults.
You aren't yet.
Well done! 4 for her first schedule.
Why did she change major? What
happened between you?
Stop your innuendo.
You're too close to them!
I killed her, is that what you think?
And what I did-
Whoa! Four hours of detention I'm
I'm giving you, let me watch.
- Good morning.
Phil Bernadet, a professor.
Mr. Murat is paranoid, yeah?
Well, paranoids often have
good reason to be.
Did Claire's departure surprise you?
I said nothing.
- Where are you going?
A class, it seems.
Hold hold hold;
I'm working too, even if you
can't see it.
Listen, Claire was a passionate,
endearing student
who was brilliant but unpredictable.
Unpredictable doesn't rhyme
with "controlled."
So you know my nickname, "the guru."
The origin of "guru" is "guide,"
a teacher.
A good teacher is the one who
knows nothing precisely.
Where were you last night between
10 pm and midnight?
At mine.
Is there a witness?
No.
- That's stupid.
That's how it is!
Yes, but it's stupid.
- You asked.
Maude? It's me.
I'm coming home.
- Tell me frankly:
did you ever suspect Murat of
inappropriate behavior?
Never.
- Who's speaking, the stepmother
or the principal protecting her
school's reputation?
Your wife.
How's your investigation?
I'm not idle, with 492 students.
Talk to Rufus.
Rufus? The nutcase?
- He threatened
a friend with a knife.
- Yeah? Why?
We were crossing his land,
it's a shortcut.
Yeah; that's not stupid.
Thanks for the tip, honey!
NO TO THE AGRICULTURE
SCHOOL EXPANSION
ACTION
"Elections, not words."
He's not wrong.
SOLIDARITY LIBERTY The
ECOLOGY REVOLUTION revolutionary!
MILITIA EVERYWHERE The
JUSTICE NOWHERE revolutionary!
With his big barracks!
Sol-i-dar-i-ty with
pen-si-o-ners!
"Militia everywhere, justice nowhere!"
All the "autographs."
Anybody there?
Ho!
Anyone?
Whoa!
What do you want?
- Hey-I'm the heat!
I didn't see.
- Thanks for the welcome?
Is it OK you bomb people, like
a wingless plane?
I was kidding.
High fashion humor?
And the knife kids say you had,
that was for laughs too?
Well, it wasn't funny.
But they hit me on the noggin with
their two-wheelers.
I wouldn't have hurt them.
Coffee?
- I wouldn't mind one.
And better than at "the
warden's", huh?
Is she the one who ratted me out?
Pfft, not even.
Look: not the biggest.
- Not the smallest.
Put yourself in my place.
- Show me.
You don't like the school.
It's been 15 years since they built it
on unbuildable land.
What a crock!
It's not common, believe it
if you want,
if you know what I mean.
I wanted to ask if you know her,
the little one: "Rosa Luxembourg."
Yes? No?
You're here because you were
told about a knife?
No, for the wolf in the sheep fold
who killed this sheep, this morning.
Never seen her in my life.
Yeah? Swear?
- Swear.
You're sure?
The fantasy:
Rufus the sociopath, the marginalized.
The psychopath. It's real life.
"There is never anything left of
the lived experience."
"Some grain will oxidize its paraffin."
Yes, Castel. What's the matter?
The young girl and Murat weren't
just teacher and student.
Listen to what she sent him:
We think alike.
But you started earlier.
And it's as if
you waited for me.
- Fuck.
What are you doing?
Come on!
Yeah yeah yeah.
- Let go of me!
Leave him alone!
It's fine!
Don't worry!
You have to calm down!
So...
Kids!
And it's as if
you had waited for me.
You're right.
Everything will change. Those able
to adapt will survive.
Nothing will last.
Let's live the present together.
I saw those videos.
I'm not afraid of the night,
of the sun.
I'm not afraid of your body that
envelops me to disappear.
I'm afraid of myself-
- Goodbye!
It's a personality cult. A real Stalin!
It wasn't for me.
- Yes? Why didn't you tell me?
Out of respect for Claire, to preserve
her privacy.
Like Stalin, Mao:
protector of youth.
And why did this young girl skip
your classes?
I wanted to explain to her
she was confusing love and
admiration.
Poor kid,
she declared her feelings and got
a punch in the nose.
It must have been awkward.
She was mortified, she felt belittled.
You might have stopped
the thing from the outset.
I should have.
- "I should have."
Yes, but it's so easy
to impress a teen when you're
her father's age.
and take advantage
of the kid maybe.
No way, I never took "advantage."
Never?
A teacher-student relationship is
never equal to equal.
The adult has authority.
It was up to you to quickly say Stop.
I chose to ignore her messages.
So that she would get tired of it.
That's it.
You wanted to play Nabokov by
Lolita-ing the kid.
And then make a date that goes wrong.
- No.
No?
- No!
You wouldn't be the first.
- Good. anyway-
for the lie by omission we'll put
0 out of 20. OK?
Get me my stuff.
- Stuff...
Yeah, we're going to sample your DNA
and compare it with hers.
Voila. Thank you so much.
Mouth open-MOUTH OPEN!
Close your eyes, it will slide in better.
There!
No, not in there, it's too small.
He'll fit. Go on!
Watch your hands!
It won't do to lash out at my colleague.
It's nothing to do with him.
Hey, give me that scarf.
We're not playing Hangman.
And forget the coffee.
Put that away.
A complete map...
We need to trace the guy.
I've received the geolocation data
on her phone.
So?
- No connection with Murat.
You're a pessimist, you know that?
No? Me neither.
This is the last sector where her
phone pinged.
Let's go around the corner.
- Yes.
Question the locals. Considering
everything, it will go quickly.
I'll come back for you.
- Where are you going?
You do your sector,
I'll do the penultimate one where
she last texted.
Thank you, nice.
Walking will do you good.
- Sure.
Going... and: bye.
Sir! Gendarmerie.
What are you doing here?
I live there.
In there?
- Yes.
Teacher salaries have gone down?
Good smell!
It's compost.
Corpse compost, does that
work too?
In the USA they're going to
legalize it.
Big business, huh?
I'm here because
my colleagues tell me Claire's phone
pinged around here yesterday.
Yes, I saw her.
That's why. What did she want?
Well, advice.
- About?
She changed major and had
fallen behind.
She wanted to talk to me about it.
- Yes, I understand.
I understand.
So, suddenly: bang!
You went into this RV to discuss
something special with her?
Are you kidding?
I only know the students in
my class.
Yeah, why I'm looking for you.
Well then; what happened?
Nothing. She didn't insist, and left.
She left...
Who are you calling?
A colleague.
To search down to your skin.
Yeah, it's me!
We're going to do a search.
It's an RV. Bring 2 or 3 people.
Yeah. No, the man is scared.
You're the last to have seen her,
we have to.
Go on, ciao.
Coffee?
Here you are!
Sorry, Captain.
- It's over there. Chop-chop!
A call. Who's calling me?
Eh?
Well? A date, Oscar?
Glass dust and a shard in
her left arch.
She may have fallen on broken glass.
It remains to be seen if it's
glass for food...
Elementary, my dear Oscar.
...or glass from a building.
Thanks, honey. Ciao.
What?
Prepared to lose?
- And you?
Ha, that's my business.
I'm a teacher.
In my job reputations are fragile,
when the knives come out.
Yeah?
Did Murat ever find the knives
were out for him?
Let's say for him gossip was
a way of life.
Or death.
Get a photo there.
There.
Up there.
And one there.
Funny, it smells
like being back in school.
Fresh and clean.
- I clean it every week.
Since the Covid? Yeah...
Sweet!
Is it a weapon?
A vacuum.
Yeah, very good! Gregory,
take a picture.
So; boring.
Big and boring.
Where does he think he is?
No!
Stop!
Yeah what?
Yes.
- Yeah?
Let me...
Not his fingerprints?
Or his DNA?
Why was he as tight as a thong?
We don't know.
Yeah, so long.
There you are.
You forgot me.
You were to come back.
- I lied.
Anything new?
No, it's the middle of nowhere.
The farmers saw nothing.
We're not going to get there.
Do you know the Coue method?
Coue?
- Yes.
"Repeat after me" -
We...
- We...
Articulate! We...
- We.
Going...
- Going.
We are going...
- To get there?
How did you know?
You think it's funny?
Me, I found that.
In the records at Menard.
His little Achilles heel.
- Open!
He's just yelling. It starts to annoy me.
Open the door.
- Deborah!
Call Ghostbusters!
Nightmares to declare?
What now?
Who is this "Deborah" you've been
yelling for?
Deborah Fournier. She has nothing
to do with this.
Were you together?
Not that night.
- So sleep.
Go on, shut it. Bye.
VETERINARY CLINIC
See you in 2 days.
Thank you.
- Bye.
Madam.
These biscuits are good!
Gendarmerie, I need to talk.
- I have nothing to hide.
Sure? OK.
Your sexual intercourse
with Mr. Murat:
how was it? Forceful? Missionary?
Omnipres-
Where is Yannick?
Thppt!
Do you know Claire Duret?
Is this about her?
I knew her.
From where? How did you meet?
- Thanks to a wild boar.
Claire found him injured in
the forest as a baby.
I'm keeping him while waiting to
find a park or a zoo.
Can't keep a wild animal at home.
Did she know that?
I'm being sued. I'll have to
put him down.
Not really!
- If I'm forced to by the court.
He's beautiful! Caring for beautiful
beasts is proof you're human.
Claire must have loved it.
To her it was a forest creature,
she wanted to find a specialist lawyer.
To her this animal symbolized anti-hunting.
But hunters are also your customers.
Voices were raised, you fought...
What are you suggesting?
You're right. Chicks aren't going to
fight over a wild pig.
But a human pig? A guy, for example.
What guy?
Yes, she adored Mr. Murat.
He didn't tell you! Damn that's stupid.
A girl in love with a teacher, how boring.
Boring to death.
Where were you Tuesday night?
Only here, a post-operative followup.
Forget about the patient's testimony:
a high-strung Malinois.
A Malinois who thinks he's mal!
She doesn't like pig jokes.
Do you like them?
You have a beautiful chapka. We're cousins!
Come on, move.
Dammit.
Christophe, can you get the door for me?
Take off my glasses;
put them in my car.
How are you, Brian?
Be proud of me.
- Why?
I've become optimistic.
- You're worrying me.
I dug elsewhere.
- Your grave?
About the vet-
- Well?
She's the daughter of a farmers
market couple who, 40 years ago-
Kidnapped a child.
Not pretty.
Guess the baby's first name.
- Alexis?
Yannick.
- What?
Yannick!
Yannick, as in-
- Shh, shh.
OK.
At the time he was called
Yannick Le Sommer.
Summer, as in Donna? Not bad.
Look at this. Pardon me.
Hey, my coffees!
It's him?
"Legal emancipation
at 16 years old, change of surname."
"For legitimate reason." Article 61
of the Civil Code.
Clever you. Didn't he want his
parents' name?
They forgot him in a parking lot.
- No!
Where he was kidnapped.
Come and eat.
Open it up.
- Where are we going?
Not where I expected.
I'm not carrying this alone.
No, but how!
Does it remind you of anything?
No?
Yeah, so open the door.
Come on.
What does this have to do with
Claire's death?
I don't know, let's look.
Give me a hand with your foot.
There we go.
This is where they chained
and gagged me.
I thought I was dying.
Hence the claustrophobia.
Your parents would've paid
the ransom?
Sure, to give themselves a
clear conscience.
Because I didn't exist for them.
Well, I'm surprised, crazy
people leaving a
7-year-old kid, by the highway,
is beyond the pale.
So a farm couple,
so nice, "Sure, we'll take you to
your mom and dad."
I followed them.
They were broke, I was manna
from heaven.
Amen.
I ran away into the forest.
Is there a reason you didn't
come back?
A place became available at
the agriculture college, like a sign.
I was a teacher, I never returned.
Out of fear.
- Of the kidnappers?
No, they're dead.
Yes, good.
But you attracted their daughter.
Deborah; raised by a foster family.
- Yeah.
We had crappy parents in common.
A good basis for a relationship.
You know that "80% of abusive adults
suffered child abuse."
And you suspect me.
There's resilience too, though.
A strength.
And then there's...
- Umm... my DNA?
You're lucky, there was none on Claire.
It's better for you. Let's go.
Something happened. A gendarme
came by.
She's on my back.
Why?
- Because of the videos.
No, keep it open, I need to breathe.
What videos?
You know how she was:
passionate, excessive.
Romantic.
I tried to explain to her she
mixed up everything.
but she wouldn't let it go.
What's that look?
- You slept with her.
With Claire?
Don't you start!
- Calm down.
Do you know where the gendarme
took me?
Your parents' barn!
- Why?
She thinks I'm twisted, like you!
Stop it.
You know I love you, Yannick.
Captain Marleau?
- There.
Captain? I have a lead for you.
How nice. To stop me suspecting
you, or Mr. Murat?
You're talking shit!
You're losing your temper. Sit down,
and no swearing.
Go slowly.
Last year, I reported a case of a spaniel
subjected to extreme violence.
The owner, Raymond Blier, was
fined €30,000.
Son of a him!
This guy should serve as a
pharmaceutical lab guinea pig.
His daughter Oriane was in a
class with Claire Duret.
And the kid ratted out
the motherfucker?
I got the daughter's account
from her friends,
so I made a report on her behalf.
Shit.
- What?
Raymond Blier is still in prison, with
no release papers.
He wasn't the one who took revenge.
- No.
His daughter?
Oriane Blier?
Hey, whoa!
Take it easy with your hammer.
Gendarmerie, like. Do you know
Claire Duret?
My best girlfriend.
Best dead girlfriend.
Where are you?
Already your break?
I'm not talking to a cop.
They've done us enough harm.
Well, first we say une cop.
And this cop tells you your father is in
the slammer because of Claire,
who informed on him.
And you left school to work
because of her too.
But you know this.
His life went bust, he blames the whole
world for being in jail.
I didn't think she would report him.
You argued?
- Yes.
Hence your message: "Watch out
for hunting accidents."
No.
- No? Wasn't that you?
Be careful, because I'll
go check it out.
She was ruining our lives, OK?
My father isn't a sadist.
Claire shouldn't have.
Done what?
- Fling the shit, like.
That motherfucker was hitting his dog!
And you let it happen;
you collaborated.
Where were you
Tuesday evening, between 10 pm
and midnight?
Working.
Ask my colleague. 11 hours for
a car rally.
Yeah, I will ask!
That's good! There! Let's go!
He's not bad.
We won't have another jerkoff!
Load of manure; come on!
Slack! Slack!
I quit. Sorry.
Why?
Are you in the tourney?
To beat Bernardet's team, yes.
Not with us.
- I'm not forcing you.
Sorry.
They're idiots.
- Well...
Hey! Minds can change!
Your guru is a loser,
like Charles Manson.
- Shut up, Fabien!
If you had opened your eyes maybe
your girlfriend wouldn't be dead.
Let him go! Leave him alone!
What'd you do?
Stop.
Come to the infirmary.
- I'd rather die!
What a bonehead.
Oriane!
Did the gendarme question you?
What gendarme?
- Come here.
Come see something.
I said nothing.
I hope so, for I'd be sad if something
happened
and your dad went back to jail
for his aggression.
I learned some stuff about him
on the Net.
I can do this.
- No, it's fine.
It's so beautiful.
What is it, dear?
- I'm sorry.
What is it?
- How could I not see it?
It was evident there was a risk of abuse.
What happened between them?
What are you talking about?
With Murat.
Nothing, surely.
She preferred acting to complaining.
We must honor her memory, OK?
Jules.
- Let go of me!
Wait; when exactly does this end?
- Drop it.
You know things-
- And you?
Mr. Murat!
A teacher is not a friend
or brother.
It's not clear what you are
to kids,
and you didn't help my
daughter's life.
I'll go, Mr. Duret.
- What happened at
your last school? They fired
you, right?
No, I decided to leave.
- Then why are you here?
Get out!
I SAID, GET OUT!
Aiee!
Achoo!
Working overtime?
I'm learning the trade.
What do you want now?
According to your coworkers' statements
you left here at around 2200 hours.
Where were you? Smoke break?
- Yeah.
Did you smoke the whole pack?
Because you were gone
more than 30 minutes.
- OK, I went to the Duret's.
voila!
I'm understanding better.
Did you go to fix their window?
To bury the hatchet.
- Well, Pocahontas;
why didn't you tell me?
There was no one home.
Or she didn't come to the door.
No. She wasn't there.
We're closing.
Well-
What a welcome, thanks!
Are you freaking out?
Or is it my colleague who's scary?
No one scares me, okay?
Let's get off to a good start.
All right?
Claire was your best friend,
she must've told you
about Mr. Murat.
No, never.
What did you think of the "guru"?
He wasn't my teacher.
And as a guy?
He checked me out sometimes.
- He threatened you?
Threatened? Why?
It was flattering.
It's a network of gerontophiles!
SLAUGHTERHOUSES
Jules? Calm down.
Don't move, I'm coming!
What did you do?
- I screwed up.
I could have succeeded.
Succeed at what?
Claire wanted to take the
slaughterhouse director hostage.
To expose the cruelty.
It hurts, I need treatment.
Foolish!
"The teacher at the slaughterhouse."
Was that the message?
Thanks, you can go.
What were you doing there?
I suspected Jules was preparing
something.
What are you doing to them? To their heads?
One dead, one injured.
It's easy to blame me.
What about the parents?
- All right!
Two students per class will
suffer incest,
but abandoning a kid by the
highway is rare.
You, I mean.
Wasn't the hostage-taking your idea?
Certainly not.
It was Claire's idea.
Mental. In short, always wrong.
What other bad ideas did she have?
I don't know.
- Think.
Well... the boar.
The one at the vet?
Claire wanted to hide it
so it wouldn't be shot.
Deborah calmed her down.
- Poor animal.
The pig.
Good. Take the bracelets
off him, please.
The investigating judge will summon
you on the break-in.
Be careful, I'm watching you.
Not like you watch teens.
Don't say that.
- Everyone says it.
Look, of course I notice certain
situations around me...
One thinks about things.
...high school students.
- Even better!
But because of what they give off,
something that sets them apart in
the eyes, their attitude,
or character... but not how
you mean it.
You mean if I had you for a teacher,
I wouldn't have failed?
- You failed?
Where are they?
- The board has fired you.
But without proof?
- The break-in at the slaughterhouse,
dangerous statements.
- I hoped you'd support me.
I did. There's too much.
Bernardet! Don't pretend you
don't see me.
You wouldn't have written to the board
to force me out?
I could have but it's not worth it.
You did it to yourself.
EMERGENCY
Hey, Julot!
The gendarme.
My son won't say anything.
- Our son.
Not without a lawyer.
- Why?
Mr. Murat is responsible for the
slaughterhouse,
he manipulated my son.
- Our son.
Family solidarity? That's right,
of course!
You want a lawyer and a scapegoat.
I want the girl's murderer. Do you
want more corpses?
Of course not.
"Of course not."
You want to be called to the morgue?
- No more.
"No more"? So come with me.
- Fuck.
What's with the "fuck"?
Stop being rude.
You need a physiotherapist.
Good god, they shouldn't be allowed
to talk to you like that.
In.
Why bring me back here?
My parents are waiting for me.
To succeed, you have to abort
your parents.
Let that sink in, OK?
Little question:
the slaughterhouse raid, who
thought of it?
You or Claire?
Claire.
It was like her hobby.
And your hobby, was it her?
No, she wasn't my girl.
You wanted her to be both
girl and friend.
She refused, you killed her.
Not at all.
I didn't kill her.
I'm wondering something: why didn't
she choose you?
Do you know who she liked best?
- No.
You don't know?
Who?
- No.
Who...
No!
Not him?
- No, not him.
Good, listen to something for
two minutes.
You don't want to be
an informer, fine.
But I will go with my
favorite theory.
Jail is for him or for you, choose.
Murat.
I saw him with Claire the night
she died.
That's it.
You gave in fast, you wouldn't have
made a good Resistance fighter.
Golly.
Are you resigning?
They're forcing me, I'll respond.
Resisting is really good.
I can go?
- Yes.
You forgot something.
- What?
In front of your door, it's dirty,
you have to sweep.
I didn't do anything.
Yet you didn't tell me you saw
Claire the night of the murder:
lie by omission.
It's a lot, no?
Hey! Wait for me.
I jostled a gendarme.
Are you stopping me?
- Don't tempt me.
Who told you I saw Claire?
Someone who told me it
was happening.
Wow!
It's nice,
a little secret date.
- Jules told you!
He was jealous, suspicious, so
he followed me.
I wanted to see her to convince her
to come back to class, but she avoided me.
She never visited?
- Until that day.
Are you following us?
- No, I was walking around.
She was about to crack.
I made a 7 pm appointment to talk
with her.
OK; 7pm, time of the crime.
So what happened?
Claire was in a hurry to be elsewhere.
And as she was leaving...
What?
- She kissed me,
like a goodbye kiss.
Castel, at 7 pm Claire was with Murat.
Does that sound weird to you?
Someone said-what was it?
Not possible. At 7pm her phone was
in the middle of the countryside.
So someone stole it.
All right, love?
- Yeah.
Say, about the Claire thing:
after coming here,
why didn't she have her phone?
I don't know,
she dropped it?
Of course.
- Hello.
That doesn't bother you,
does it?
Why so nervous during the search?
That's why you pay me!
You've no reason to get all defensive.
Move, you can explain it to me.
Don't bother, no one's going to
steal your stuff.
So long, love.
- Bye.
Yeah.
No handcuffs?
- If you want.
You think you're in an American movie.
Here, do it yourself.
Handcuffs!
Is he going to last a long time?
What?
I didn't kill her.
So much the better, one less suspect.
Let's say someone else killed her:
before she died, what'd you do?
I took her mobile.
Why, for the plan?
- What?
For her plan?
No...
When she changed majors,
I thought it had something to
do with Yannick.
Something distasteful?
At the end of a class, she forgot
her mobile.
You stole it?
No, I stopped-I looked at
the files on it.
You're not "juleferryien."
- What?
She knew it was me, I was the
last one in the room.
So that's why she went to see you,
She wanted to snitch on you,
and you killed her.
- No.
I got rid of it.
The body?
- The phone! Shit!
Hey, no big words.
Wipe your nose.
There's where you abandoned me.
- See, I came back.
There's the pond.
The pond? It's about time.
So; one, two;
well...
Shall I go?
- Yes.
Pay attention!
Isn't that a bit far?
- No.
I have colleagues you will stay
like that for hours.
There, I found it.
See, I was telling the truth.
The truth is you obstructed the
investigation,
that won't cut it.
Help me, I'm not gonna do
all the work.
There it is, here.
Captain?
- What?
There, I recovered the SIM card data.
How did you do it?
- It wasn't me.
It was my 12 year old daughter,
she's got the fingers.
Twelve? She'll go far.
If she doesn't meet a pervert.
Or become paranoid, like her father.
Now then.
There's a text message in Drafts
from the day before her death.
NO RECIPIENT:
SAMANTHA LORD IS RETURNING SOON
"Samantha Lord"? Who's that?
Anybody here?
Banzai.
Awww, it's "cute," a small fireplace!
Awww, a Christmas tree!
Piano, candle!
It's romantico-erotic tonight.!
I'm not disturbing you.
- As always.
I wasn't asking. Sit down, sir!
Thanks, I'd rather not.
- Is that so.
I wanted to know... how do you play this?
...no. I wanted to know:
who's Samantha Lord?
Samantha Lord was an Australian
activist from the 70s,
who committed burglaries to
finance her
pro-environment work.
You talked about her in your classes?
I cited her as an activist
of action.
- That's it.
The kid wanted to imitate your example.
Or look like the ideal woman.
You can watch while I make
the scallops.
The girl in the kitchen,
what a macho cliche.
Good! So...
Last time, you said the kid looked
as if she was
in a hurry, but for what?
I don't know.
Hey, it's good, huh?
Neither do I.
Maybe in a hurry to kidnap
the oinker?
Huh, Mama Deborah?
- By herself? A 100kg animal?
You would've prevented it.
No, I should have helped her,
denounce the slimy hunt.
Animal welfare and climate change
were her avocation.
If all young people were like her,
the planet would be better.
Well I agree with you.
But didn't you say she wanted to
hire environmental lawyers?
An environmental lawyer, but she
couldn't afford it.
'How would she have paid for it'
is the question.
Maude!
What are you doing here?
- You're not going to crack,
and let me down?
Why do you say that?
You don't Mr. Murat to pay.
But...
Do you have the bracelet?
- Yes.
Let's see it.
- Here you go. Why do you want it?
What do you see? A bracelet
with a stamped eagle's head.
At least 18 carats, it's worth a cool sum.
They say it was too big, why wear it,
she could lose it.
Why was she wearing it that night?
What's your conclusion?
- Who would have stolen from
their parents to pay a top
environmental lawyer?
Samantha Lord.
For a wild boar?
- Maybe not her,
but imagine a teenage girl, 17,
a little militant, a little idealistic.
And adoptive mother of a wild pig.
Who do you see?
She wouldn't let her oinker get killed.
What are you thinking about?
Is her death my fault?
I encouraged her with no supervision.
Don't beat yourself up.
We got by when we were young, but
not all kids can adapt.
I heard you were laid off.
How?
- A neighbor hears things.
I wanted to tell you, if a fight
is necessary,
start a petition, I can canvass for it.
Don't hesitate to ask me.
That's nice of you, but I'll be fine.
- I won't insist.
If the cops won't leave you alone,
I could-
No, everything's worked out there, thanks.
Weird. We've never spoken before.
Always ready to defend the widows
and orphans.
♪ My reassuring danger,
my excess of madness ♪
♪ aside from nothing, the
cards of my life ♪
It's Catherine Lara, not Mozart's Requiem.
♪...to cursed lovers. ♪
You loved your step-daughter daughter.
A €1,000 bracelet!
- €2,300,
I had it appraised.
Did the kid know that?
- I think so.
The one you told me about?
- Yes.
Can I see?
- Why yes.
Did you see her with it?
No, I'd have liked to.
It's magnificent.
You did so much.
- She was wonderful.
Dad going out with the principal
was a bit complicated for her.
Not your fault you're in love.
How did you both meet?
- He didn't want Claire to go to
an agricultural school.
She forced him to see it.
We visited.
- And its charm worked.
He registered Claire, and asked me out.
So, the family jewels:
where are they now?
Well-
What?
No, nothing.
Well.
Was it in here?
- Yes.
You keep the gift boxes?
She didn't want the box, she wanted
to wear the bracelet.
But it was too big.
- All the same.
She didn't steal it?
Not at all. Ridiculous!
- Me, ridiculous?
Let me look.
I know, it's because of the hat.
Anyway, I know a picked lock
when I see one.
Mirror, who's the biggest fibber
of all, the stepmom?
What? Would Maude have killed Claire
for this jewelry
without even taking it?
- True, it's not very logical.
This mirror sucks.
Furthermore, you're right,
she wouldn't have moved the body,
a body is heavy.
It takes two.
Catherine Lara!
That's nice.
"Requiem For A Love."
You know who's listening to this?
What's-his-name,
Mr. Rufus. He lives next door
to the school.
Captain?
- Go ahead.
Are you going to see him?
- Why, shouldn't I?
We were together at one time,
when I first started teaching.
YOU AND THE-you were seeing the
old butt, the anarchist?
Grade A, like you.
The angst. Was it back on?
I think so. Yes.
*This* started up again, Claire knew
about it and died.
I love my husband, I'm not
cheating on him.
Well, Rufus has no luck.
- Captain?
It's true that
coming back to try again.
- To your house?
The night of the murder?
- No!
Come on, I'm not going to his place.
I'll say no more.
We doing this tournament,
or what?
Don't be boring.
We could've done without the
slaughterhouse.
I did it for Claire.
- She didn't ask anything of you.
What do you want?
I thought about your proposition.
OK, I forgot.
I thought you were just being polite.
- Wait.
Good...
What we could do is talk about your
firing on social networks,
I have a dozen aliases.
Come in, come in.
Tell me about yourself so we can
make you a positive profile.
It creates empathy.
It'd suit you if they accuse me.
Yesterday you came looking for info.
Are you here for that, now? Huh?
You suspect me over nothing.
A young girl died, I remind you!
Yeah, and you feel a little responsible.
You're obsessed with this school.
Yes, for 15 years.
Those photos
prove it's a nuisance.
I've had it up to here.
You'll burn them?
- Yeah, yeah.
Even Claire?
I have no pictures of Claire.
She wasn't into me.
You old asshole.
Do you think I killed your darling?
The investigation interests you.
Yeah, I'm curious.
Sorry, I'm a suspect, so I take it
out on the innocent.
No hard feelings?
Maude?
Where are you going?
We have the inter-class tournament.
Are you going to golf?
No, I'm missing a driver, I wonder
where it's gone.
We'll look for it together.
The Petit-Clarart Killing.
Is this an OAS hideout?
Good evening, sir! Are you in?
You're not the killer. Satisfied?
- What do you want?
I said to myself, it's weird since
she's not guilty,
so how come she freaked out when
I questioned her?
I leave when I'm done.
And you'll see if my hand goes along.
Liar, you lied
when you said Claire wasn't at
home that night.
Haven't you seen an illicit couple
that includes a gentleman
high school hunter?
I can't count on anyone.
You can count on me. Promise,
swear, spit.
There was a 4x4 at the house,
with a man.
- Who?
He threatened me,
I'm to say nothing.
This guy has a screw loose.
A box is missing.
He's watching me.
Who was it?
Was it Rufus Cordelier? Is that who?
Is it?
It's him.
He's got a big mouth and small arms.
Cordelier's a sentimentalist,
don't be afraid.
Gendarmerie!
Hey! Gendarmerie!
- Hey, hey...
We're conducting a search.
- Go, get out!
Whoa, hey, no no no! Stay here!
It's Murat's bike.
Murat!
Here you are!
I thought he killed you!
It's OK, it's over. Sit down.
You're all green.
I don't understand; I understand
nothing.
A minute! There you go.
I wanted to play gendarme.
Well done! You needed to
trust me.
Did you come to avenge her?
I know everything.
Everything!
You all right?
- No.
I'll get water.
Come on, stick to him!
Breathe!
Come on, stick to him! Isabelle,
stick to him! Good!
Well done!
Watch him! Go, go!
Stick to him!
Rhythm.
He's going!
Rhythm!
Come on!
Look.
It's the cops.
Well, what?
Aren't you going out the front door?
Come, I know how to be discreet.
Hee hee!
Gendarmerie! Let us pass.
You didn't mention that he threatened
a student with a knife.
We were counting on you in
the investigation.
What was he doing at your place the
night of the murder?
He wasn't.
He wasn't there.
Maybe Rufus stole the jewelry
while she was out;
Her stepdaughter surprised him-
He killed her.
- That works.
And when the lady realizes Rufus
is the killer,
she says nothing and covers for him,
for old time's sake-you follow me?
Or out of guilt, for dumping him.
- That's it;
that's it, right?
No answer.
No problem: we'll take the DNA
from his van.
We'll find evidence Claire was in it,
alive or dead.
By the way, where did he kill her,
the woods?
It's not him.
"It's not him"!
It's not him; well shit then.
If by chance it's not him:
in fairy tales, heteronormative sexist
ones of course,
if the killer isn't Prince Charming, it's?
The stepmother.
- And that works.
I returned earlier than expected.
A broken window, something
had happened.
I remembered the threats
against Claire.
The power was out.
Someone had entered.
Claire?
*Hello?*
I knew you would call me back.
It's over for me.
*What?*
I killed her.
- *Who?*
Antoine's daughter.
*I'm coming.*
The daughter of my love.
It's not your fault, you didn't
do it on purpose.
You didn't know it was her.
What does it change?
Antoine knew it was tense between
her and me.
That's why you called Rufus?
- He told me to keep quiet.
He told me to keep quiet, it was an
accident and I couldn't bring Claire back.
A principal who kills a student;
I let myself be led.
It's his fault. He cleans everything up,
tells you to stay quiet,
moves the body. What he wouldn't
do for her!
The man is crazy.
The stupid thing is that he didn't
see the bracelet had fallen off.
By leaving an empty box in my
jewelry drawer-
You made it appear that she
had boosted it.
She wasn't stupid:
she made believe there was a
burglary, by breaking the window.
But she had glass shards on her face.
I would have given her the damn
bracelet. But I lied.
A pig with a lawyer would be a surprise.
She didn't need money,
she needed attention and listening.
Right?
- Right.
Right.
Your wife wanted to denounce herself.
But she turned to Rufus.
To say nothing and not go down
for Claire.
It's my fault, I should have understood
my daughter better.
A little means a lot in life, remember
the happy parts.
Captain?
How is this?
"Her age escaped childhood, laughing
like innocence."
Where's this from?
- An 18th century poem,
for her headstone next to
her mother's.
It's nice.
Block the penetration!
No, none of that!
Yeah, "keep away"!
Move there!
Guard!
That's a foul!
It was a pivot! No way!
That's not OK! They're not bad kids!
They're not Islamo-leftists, right?
Get back on defense!
That's right!
Work it!
That's sick.
Go, go, go, replace him!
So, he fills them with his green fantasies?
Who said anything about fantasies?
Bless you, my children.
Hey, break it up, voyeur!
Bye, Captain!
No way! Pass the ball! Pass the ball!
You dummies!