Holy Ghost, come to me. Praise God.
Praise God. Move up on me, Holy Ghost.
Praise God.
This here sinner repents.
Holy Ghost, move up on me. Protect me
and mine with your quickening power.
(rattling)
Holy Ghost, come to me.
Help me, Jesus!
Help me, Jesus! Help me, Jesus!
(Mulder) Not as far as you know.
Right. Not this time of year.
All right. Thank you, Doctor. Goodbye.
Snakes.
Lots and lots of snakes.
Very pissed off ones, from the look of it.
It's the former Mr Jared Chirp,
of McMinn County, Tennessee.
- Oh, my God.
- 116 separate bite marks.
Judging from the wounds, there were 50
snakes involved - copperheads and rattlers.
It says here he was found dead in his car.
With a pistol in his hand. He fired six shots,
into the floorboards, even into his kneecap.
- The windows were shut, the doors locked.
- But what happened to all the snakes?
No one seems to know that.
There was not a scale found.
I just got off the phone with a herpetologist,
and he's stumped.
Especially because rattlesnakes
tend to hibernate in winter.
So you think that Mr Chirp was murdered?
It would appear that way,
but the question is, how?
There's no physical evidence.
No tyre tracks, no footprints.
I can't see how anyone
could have done this. And then, why?
Why use poisonous snakes
as a murder weapon?
Maybe it's symbolic. I mean, serpents
and religion have gone hand in hand.
They've represented
the temptation of Eve, original sin.
They've been feared throughout history,
as they've been thought to embody Satan,
to serve evil itself.
Maybe these ones actually do.
These particular serpents
actually were serving evil?
Are you gonna type that
on our travel request?
No. But, at the very least, this case
does seem to centre around religion.
And you're not the only one
to think that, by the way.
Jared is in a better place now, Gracie.
He's at peace.
You know Reverend Mac:key's right, honey.
He is in a better place.
Reverend Samuel Mackey?
My name is Fox Mulder. This is Dana Scully.
We're with the FBI. May we speak with you?
Come on, Gracie. Let's get you home.
We apologise for our timing. We'd like
to ask a few questions about Jared Chirp.
I've already spoken to the sheriff about it.
Though I'm not sure that was a good idea.
Specifically, you had suspicions
about the manner in which he died?
I should be the last one to point a finger
or say a harsh word.
Our church is founded on acceptance
and tolerance of all people, all beliefs.
But?
Before Jared joined us, he belonged to a
fundamentalist congregation outside of town,
the Church of God with Signs & Wonders.
It practises snake handling.
As a sign of faith, worshippers
handle deadly snakes and drink poison.
They believe that the Holy Spirit
protects the righteous.
Jared grew up in that church,
but it is very difficult to walk away
from a belief system that one is raised in.
- It takes great courage.
- Why did he walk away?
He and Gracie, his girlfriend, left it together.
They found that a rigid interpretation
of the Bible was not for them.
Especially when it involves risking
life and limb in the act of worship.
But again, it is not for me to judge.
I will say, however,
that both Jared and Gracie
were persecuted by
the members of their former church.
All this animus stems from
their church leader, Enoch O'Connor.
Animus enough to motivate a murder?
Snake handling -
didn't learn that in catechism class.
That's funny. I knew a couple of Catholic
schoolgirls who were expert at it.
Enoch O'Connor? Federal agents.
- Where's the light switch?
- The nearest one? Probably ten miles away.
Rattlesnakes and
medieval visions of damnation.
I, for one, feel a whole lot closer to God.
I don't know, Scully.
When you get right down to it,
is snake handling any harder to buy into than
communion wafers or transubstantiation?
Or believing in flying saucers.
I'm just saying that your faith and O'Connor's
seem to be based on the same book.
Uh-oh, Scully. What do you think
O'Connor keeps in here?
Something slithery?
- It's all right. It's empty.
- Why is it empty?
(rattling)
(door opens)
By what right are you here?
Reverend Enoch O'Connor?
We're federal agents.
We're, uh... with the FBI.
Reverend, do something
about these snakes, please.
You got nothing to fear
if you're righteous people.
Just in case we're not,
we could use a little righteous help here.
What do you want?
We're here to ask you questions about a
former member of your church, Jared Chirp.
That boy strayed from the path
and was lost to the Dark One.
I'm sorry for his soul.
There ain't much else to say.
He died from snakebites. We thought
maybe you'd have a special insight into that.
I do.
- It was a test.
- A test? What do you mean?
A test of faith.
A test of righteousness.
When the Devil aims to test you,
you best be ready.
And you sure better know
which side you're on.
Are you speaking about
the Devil's test or your test?
I don't think you people
realise which side you're on.
I do.
You can leave now.
Tennessee. Snakes.
Thank you, Mulder. Thank you so much. I say
we arrest him and catch the first flight out.
He seems a likely suspect,
only the sheriff's office ruled him out.
He was in Kentucky
the night Jared Chirp died.
There are other people in his congregation.
Chirp died with a packed suitcase by his side.
There's gotta be somebody
that knows where he was headed.
Here you go, honey.
Reverend Mackey? This might not be
the best time, but can I speak to you?
Of course.
Jared called the boarding house
late the night he died.
He wanted to talk to Gracie.
I didn't let him.
It was after two. She was sound asleep.
It sounded like the boy had been drinkin'.
He wasn't makin' any sense. He was rantin'
about seein' the Devil, and payin' for his sins.
Iris, why didn't you tell the police?
I don't know how to tell Gracie.
I kept her from speakin' to Jared
his last night on Earth.
I couldn't have known, though. I couldn't.
No, no. You couldn't have known.
I can help you talk to Gracie.
Reverend Mackey? Everybody's here.
Thank you, Gracie.
You and I will see this through, Iris,
right after study group.
Thank you.
(clapping)
(Enoch) Our God is a fearsome God.
- (man) Amen!
- (Enoch) He demands our very lives.
Revelations, three. The sixteenth verse.
'Tis better to be hot or cold than lukewarm.
Hallelujah!
Yes!
God says... if you're lukewarm,
He will vomit you out of His mouth.
Yes! Did you hear what I said?
Yes! God hates the lukewarm!
"So, because you are lukewarm,
I am about to spit you out of my mouth."
Now, that could sound pretty harsh, couldn't
it? I mean, depending on how one reads it.
But if we put this verse
in a historical context,
I think we'll see that John was specifically
addressing the problems of the Church...
God wants you hot!
God wants you on fire!
Praise to Jesus.
God wants you to put your money
where your mouth is.
- Amen!
- Hallelujah!
(rattling)
People ask me why I handle snakes.
Hallelujah!
I tell 'em. It's cos the Scripture tells me to.
Praise God!
(Reverend Mackey
lectures in the background)
Hallelujah.
Hallelujah!
(congregation sings a hymn)
Witness the power!
Witness the awesome power of God
as He blesses His people
and destroys His enemies.
Thank you, God!
(hissing)
I don't understand it. None of us
saw or heard anything. Just her scream.
When we ran in she was lying on the floor.
I cleared everybody out of the building
once I saw the bite marks, but...
Reverend, how close
was Iris to Jared Chirp?
Not particularly close, but I'd spoken
with her not 15 minutes earlier about him.
- What'd you talk about?
- She was upset.
Something about Jared calling her
the night he died, looking for Gracie.
Something about him paying for his sins.
But I don't know. We didn't get
to finish our conversation.
Maybe that was the point.
Why Iris? Why is this happening?
Gracie, we're investigating the leader
of your former church, Enoch O'Connor.
We believe that he may have had something
to do with what happened here tonight.
We would appreciate
anything you could tell us.
No, he didn't do this.
This is Satan's work, not man's.
That sounds like something that
Reverend O'Connor might say.
Now, you're not a member
of that congregation any more.
And I understand that's because
you're someone who thinks for herself.
Keeping an open mind, is it conceivable
that O'Connor could have done any of this?
No! Don't you think I would know?
Me of all people.
He couldn't have done this. He just...
(Mackey) Gracie might be biased.
O'Connor is your father.
When Gracie got pregnant...
O'Connor barred her from his church.
She and Jared Chirp.
His church and his home.
- You 00min'?
- I think I'll check around back.
"Pray for the souls... lost to us."
(rattling)
You must be judged.
Repent.
Pray for the Lord's quickening power.
By the hand of God!
(Mulder) Let her go!
Your partner could have learned
something about herself
if you hadn't have stopped me.
Some powerful good news maybe.
I'd say it's good news for you
that she's not here right now,
considering what you tried to do to her.
Is that what you did to your wife?
Alice O'Connor.
Succumbed to multiple snakebites
in June 1994.
It happened during a church service.
Or at least that's what you told local police.
You got away with it.
Almost.
What was the problem with your wife?
Was she not... righteous enough for you?
Just like your daughter's boyfriend?
Or Iris Finster?
Educated man. Too smart to know any better.
Smart enough to know you're a murderer.
Satan is near and you don't even have eyes.
You're just proud and fancy-free.
Ah, no one quite
passes muster with you, huh?
You feel the need to exact
some kind of Old Testament revenge?
What about your daughter?
What were your plans for her?
I pray for her soul.
I pray and I pray, because she's lost.
Because she no longer believes as you do?
You think, because you're educated,
you're better than most? You ain't.
Unless you're smart down here,
the Devil's gonna make a fool of you
and you ain't even gonna know it.
I changed my mind. I don't wanna see him.
Besides, I won't do any better
than you people in gettin' him to talk.
Gracie?
You still don't believe your father did it?
It don't matter what I believe.
He'll be judged as he deserves.
Can't nobody avoid it.
(rattling)
(Enoch prays)
(door opens)
Deputy found him about an hour ago.
There's no telling when he was attacked.
I guess it's looking
less and less like he's a suspect.
Unless he somehow managed to do this to
himself. As a test of his own righteousness.
If so, Mulder, the jury's still out.
I spoke to his doctor.
It's a toss-up as to whether he'll pull through.
- Anti-venom treatment?
- He's not receiving it.
- Why not?
- Gracie stepped in.
She's forbidding treatment on religious
grounds. It's not clear whether she can,
but she says that it's up to God
as to whether he lives or dies.
And you think that she may not be entirely
motivated by concern for her father's soul?
Well, more to the point,
what if she did this?
She told me that her father
would be judged as he deserves.
- This is what she meant?
- She grew up around snakes.
Who's to say she isn't every bit as adept
at handling them as he is?
I can see her being angry enough at her father
to attack him, but... what about the others?
He left in a hurry.
He packed one suitcase and a gun.
Earlier that night, he calls Gracie.
Gets Iris instead.
Starts rambling about paying for his sins.
He's frightened and wants to leave town,
presumably with Gracie.
So what's he scared of?
I don't understand how O'Connor's church
exerts a strong pull on these people.
It's not so hard to understand. It's a culture
with a very well-defined set of rules.
It's an intolerant culture.
I don't know. Sometimes a little intolerance
can be a welcome thing.
Clear-cut right and wrong,
black and white, no shades of grey.
In a society where rules are harder to come
by, some people would appreciate that.
You're saying that you would welcome
someone telling you what to believe?
I'm just saying that somebody
offering you all the answers...
can be a very powerful thing.
It's lab results.
Am I reading this right? Did Jared Chirp
have himself tested for sterility?
Which turns out to be more or less the case.
Based on this, that means that Jared
can't be the father of Gracie's baby.
Dated the day he died.
So maybe he was killed
because he discovered the truth.
(medical monitor beeps steadily)
Gracie... I'd like to ask you to reconsider.
No. This is what he'd want.
He may die without medical treatment.
I've seen him bit a dozen times.
He always said that it was up to God
whether he lives or dies.
He said it was a worse sin not to trust God.
There are many ways to trust God, Gracie.
One of them is to trust
to the miracles of doctors and medicine.
Or, in your heart...
do you really not want him to get better?
It ain't for me.
I can't risk his soul.
When you first came to me, you said
that you wanted to think for yourself.
To live your life as you saw fit.
If you stand here and let your father die,
whose beliefs are you living?
Yours?
Or his?
You're doing the right thing.
I'll go tell the doctor, OK?
(beeping quickens)
Agents! Enoch O'Connor is gone.
I was away for five minutes.
His bed's empty. Gracie is gone, too.
How could Gracie
have possibly gotten him out?
- Maybe he took her.
- He was on his deathbed. That's impossible.
- Besides, what's his motivation?
- I may be able to answer that.
Jared Chirp wasn't the father of Gracie's child.
We know that. What about it?
Enoch O'Connor is.
That's why she wanted to get away from
him and his church as fast as she could.
And I tried to teach her to forgive him.
Daddy, please!
I'm bringing you home.
Somebody help me!
In the name of our holy
and most fearsome God.
(all) Hallelujah!
Resist the Devil and he will flee.
Resist him!
Something's wrong.
Something's wrong with my baby.
Jesus, put your hands on this one.
You can heal her.
Yes, Jesus. Yes, dear Jesus.
Jesus, dear Lord.
Dear Jesus, deliver this woman.
Oh, my God. Jesus. Jesus.
No. Don't. Don't!
Dear God, dear Heavenly Father,
deliver this woman.
- No.
- Lay your hands on this woman, God.
- Yes.
- No.
No!DoNfl
Hallelujah, praise the Lord.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
Dear Jesus. Dear Jesus.
Holy Jesus! Hallelujah!
Dear Jesus! Hallelujah!
Hallelujah!
- How is she?
- Deep shock. Some loss of blood.
What happened here? Where's the baby?
- These folks aren't talkin'.
- (Mulder) Scully?
Take a look at this.
Snakes.
She gave birth to snakes?
The Devil has been cast out.
- Stay with her.
- Where are you going?
Find her father.
He's gonna wanna tie up some loose ends.
You stole what was most precious to me.
Gracie?
- She came to me on her own.
- (silent prayer)
She wanted to escape a life of fear
and judgment, of intolerance.
She fled a harsh and vengeful god.
And you.
Drop the knife!
You all right?
Daddy? Daddy?
Gracie, it's Agent Scully. We're taking
you to the doctor right now, OK?
- No. I gotta...
- Can you tell me what happened, Gracie?
- Where's my daddy?
- You're safe. My partner's gone after him.
You're gonna be OK.
He can't hurt you any more.
You don't understand.
He saved me.
I'll call for an ambulance.
Relax. Help's on the way.
No, it's not. I told you, boy.
You still don't know which side you're on.
Be smart, down here.
Yes. Please hurry.
They're on their way.
- Agent!
- It wasn't O'Connor.
It was you. You killed Jared Chirp.
- Are you joking?
- No. I'm just beginning to see it now.
Jared must have come to understand
that he wasn't the father of Gracie's baby.
That you were.
Did he confront you earlier that night,
only to see you for who you really are?
Just who is it you think I am?
Is that what happened with Iris Finster?
Was she beginning to catch on?
Is that why you killed her?
Or was it just to further frame
Enoch O'Connor?
Is that what this is really about?
Ruining O'Connor? Seducing his daughter?
Destroying him by any conceivable means?
Are you a righteous man, Agent Mulder?
Stay where you are.
It's just a simple question.
Most people believe they're
on the side of angels. But are they?
If you were put to the test...
how would you do?
(rattling)
Where's Mulder?
(Mulder) Help!
You can't help him. This is his alone.
(Scully) Mulder?
Argh!
(rattling)
- Mackey?
- Still no trace.
Even though every law enforcement agency
in Tennessee is lookin' for him.
They won't find him.
People think the Devil has horns and a tail.
They're not used to lookin'
for some kindly man.
He's just a man, Mulder. Just like O'Connor.
Not like O'Connor.
If this was some kind of test,
looks like I failed.
I'd say if it was,
you passed with flying colours.
- You're alive, aren't you?
- Proud and fancy-free.
Reverend Wells, it's a real joy
to have a man in the pulpit
who has such an open and
modern way of looking at God.
Bless you for saying so.
I won't keep you.
I just wanted to welcome you to Hamden.
Thank you.
I look forward to seeing you on Sunday.
Visiontext Subtitles: Adrian Isaac
(Child) I made this!