God's love will set us free.
And I believe...
if I pray for that love...
if I get down on my knees...
and allow God to enter my hardened,
lonely, miserable heart
and change me through and through...
that miracle... will come.
Now, who here believes that with me?
Do you?
- Do you?
- Yes, sir, I believe it.
Do you?
Well, believe... because God's love
is not just some slogan.
It's a promise... straight to you
from the Lord Almighty himself.
A promise paid for with the blood
of his only begotten son,
Jesus Christ of Nazareth.
All you have to do... is believe.
(men) Amen!
God's love will set you free.
Now, doesn't that just lift up your heart
and make you want to say "Glory! Amen!"?
Glory! Amen!
Join with me.
Allow the spirit of Jesus Christ
to show you the way
up to our heavenly Father.
Glory! Amen!
Let God's love free you from your prison
and deliver you to his side in Heaven.
Glory! Amen!
Praise his name.
Praise his holy love. Glory! Amen!
Glory! Amen!
- Glory! Amen!
Glory. Amen. Glory. Amen.
Glory. Amen. Glory. Amen...
Do you believe that, Donnie?
God loves a sack of crap like you?
The Bible says.
The Bible says you kill women, cut their
pinkies, you get to burn in hell.
- (guard) You listening to me?
- Glory. Amen.
God's got a place for you,
all right, you sick puke.
Then where's that leave you?
Sorry. It's not good enough
for the Illinois penal system.
(yells) My hands! My hands!
Life without chance of parole for the
premeditated and sadistic sexual murders
of five Twin Cities women in 1994.
Donald Addie Pf aster.
You two put this man away.
Yeah. Someone forgot
to throw away the key.
That's another story.
We have to apprehend this man.
We'd use your help in understanding
who it is we're after.
Donnie Pf aster is a death fetishist.
A collector of bone and flesh,
toenails and hair.
- It's what floats his boat, gets him off.
- He's a sick man.
We found women's fingers in his freezer.
He liked to eat them with peas and carrots.
- So it's just women he's after?
- Just women.
Five years in here thinking about that.
He's worked up quite an appetite.
I happen to know you two agents
have a thing for the supernatural.
The circumstances of the escape...
There is nothing supernatural
about this man.
Donnie Pf aster is just plain evil.
"Don't Look Any Further" by John Hiatt)
(Mulder) Case closed.
You didn't look at the file, did you?
- A man escaped from prison.
- Not a man. Donnie Pf aster.
He didn't just escape. He walked out
of a maximum-security facility
and no one seems to know how.
- Isn't that why we're here?
- That's why I'm here.
I don't know about you.
Why are you here?
- Go home, Scully.
- Mulder, this case doesn't bother me.
The man abducted you.
Donnie Pf aster did a number on your head
like I've never seen. It's OK to... walk away.
Mulder, that man does things to people that
no one should ever have to think about.
It's not a question of if I should stay.
I don't have a choice.
So let's get to work.
Well, this isn't the first incident.
Two prisoners have escaped from facilities
in neighbouring states over the past year.
At 6.06 this morning
Donnie Pf aster made it three.
6.06?
What's so supernatural about that?
Dozens of witnesses, guards and staff,
and no one seems to remember anything.
They didn't know they were missing.
- Were they apprehended?
- They haven't been seen again.
I already told the warden everything
I know... everything I saw that day.
Yes, but I'm still a little confused.
Maybe you could go over it again.
- I'm a Christian man.
- Then you'll tell me the truth.
Yeah. But I got no idea about
Donnie Pf aster... or how he broke out.
You and Donnie were in the garment shop
at the time he disappeared.
It wasn'tjust me. There was a lot of us.
Yeah, but you had something happen.
You had an incident.
Yeah. Something like that.
You cried out to the guards
that you'd cut your hands.
My fingers, man. I saw them all cut off.
- Others saw them, too.
- I felt them cut off.
- How do you explain that?
- God works in mysterious ways, brother.
Glory. Amen.
Posthypnotic suggestion.
Did you see him?
Did I see him raise his foot?
Yes, I saw that.
Programmed behaviour,
prompted by suggestion -
a rhythmic motion of the hands, producing
an unconscious act in a conscious state.
Doesn't work on you.
- I know what hypnosis is.
- Group hypnosis.
If you're suggesting
Donnie escaped from prison
using a technique from a Vegas
lounge act, I'd think again.
Mesmer was able
to hypnotise entire audiences.
So, how would Donnie
have acquired this ability?
I'm not saying that it was Donnie.
- Then who?
- Three inmates missing from three prisons.
One man has had possible contact with
each of those cons. The prison chaplain.
- "Glory. Amen."
- ("Don't Look Any Further")
Not God, the chaplain.
Scully, what?
That song, can you hear that?
Barely.
I haven't heard it since high school.
That's the second time in the last hour.
I think if it was a make-out song,
it'd be ruined for ever now, huh?
Looking for something to eat?
- Me?
- How about today's special?
- You aren't a narc, are ya?
- No.
- You're looking at my hands.
- You need a buff and polish.
What are you? A freak?
I... I just got out of prison.
Hey, Missy. Leave the customers alone!
I'll do it for free.
You just got out of prison,
and you want to give me a manicure?
I'll even do your cuticles.
(Reverend Orison) You receive
the Lord's grace and this is your thanks?
What?
(Reverend Orison)
Who do you think got you out of prison?
I don't care. I'm busy right now.
The grace of God got you out, and it's
the only thing that will keep you out.
- I thought you were kidding.
- He's chosen you, Donnie.
Later.
- You called them on me.
- No.
- Then do something.
- I have a car.
- We aren't going to make it to the car.
- It's within his power.
Glory. Amen.
(waitress screams)
- Was he here?
- Well, um... we're trying to determine that.
- Did you see him?
- Well, that's a good question.
We thought we saw something,
but apparently we didn't.
We got a call about a possible
sighting of the suspect.
- Well, something happened here, huh?
- A guy got hit by a car.
Prison chaplain, it turns out.
A Reverend Orison.
Paramedics took him to the hospital.
He's in bad shape.
("Don't Look Any Further" by John Hiatt
over stereo)
Excuse me, uh, could
you turn that up, please?
Yeah.
You're lucky to be alive, Reverend Orison.
- Who are you?
- Special Agent Dana Scully.
Believe in the Lord, Agent Scully.
He believes in you.
That's nice. My partner and I are more
concerned with several disappearances
from maximum-security facilities
that involve you.
Don't be concerned. God has them.
What do you mean?
Reverend?
- You're a believer, aren't you?
- This has nothing to do with me.
It has everything to do with you.
You have faith... have had faith.
You hear him calling you,
but you're unsure what to do.
It's not exactly a long shot, sir.
You stand as you do now,
neither here nor there.
Longing, but afraid. Waiting for a sign.
When the signs are everywhere.
What happened to the inmates, sir?
Everything has a reason, Scout.
Everything on God's earth.
Every moment of every day,
the Devil waits for but an instant.
As it is, it has always been.
The Devil's instant is our eternity.
The good reverend. How do you do?
Or maybe I should say "How do you do it?"
His is the word. I am but the
messenger who delivers it.
Well, this delivery arrived a little late.
A little late and a little cold,
as a matter of fact.
I thought you'd want to see it.
- What is this?
- Blood of the Lamb, Reverend.
The handiwork of Mr Donnie Pf aster -
a young girl he picked up at the bus stop.
- Oh, Lord.
- Where is he, Reverend?
He took my car.
- She wasn't supposed to die.
- No, Donnie was supposed to die.
You were supposed to kill him.
That's why you freed him.
God knows you're capable of it.
Reverend Orison
is really Robert Gailen Orison,
convicted in of first-degree murder.
Served 22 years in Soledad.
God spoke to me.
He told me to look after Donnie.
When God spoke to you, Reverend,
did he happen to mention
where Donnie was headed?
- Where are you going, Mulder?
- To prove that man's a liar.
How do you prove that somebody
isn't being directed by God?
- You don't believe that it happens?
- God is a spectator. He reads box scores.
- I don't believe that.
- You think God directs that man? To kill?
Donnie isn't dead. We don't know that
the other inmates who escaped are dead.
So what? You think that God directs
him to... let the prisoners out to kill?
No. But I believe that the reverend
believes what he's saying.
- That it's God working through him.
- Well, plenty of nutbags do.
Has he ever spoken to you?
- I'm trying not to take of fence.
- What did he say?
Mulder, I have heard
that song three times now.
That may not mean anything to you,
but it does to me.
- What does it mean?
- I never thought about it before.
It never meant anything, until yesterday
when it made me remember something.
What?
When I was 13, my father
was stationed in San Diego.
I was listening to that song
when my mother came in
and told me that my Sunday-school
teacher had been killed.
Oh.
He'd been murdered in his front yard.
And that's the first time that I ever felt
that there was real evil in the world.
Mulder, Reverend Orison
called me "Scout".
The same name my Sunday-school
teacher called me.
Donnie Pf aster escaped
from prison at 6.06am.
That's the same time that I
woke up yesterday morning
when my power went out.
So what do you think
that God is telling you?
All right. Come with me, Scout. I'll show
you how the reverend talks to God.
(male voice) Police are involved in
a manhunt for a prisoner who escaped
in Marion, Illinois.
He was last seen driving a green
Chevrolet Impala with a black landau top.
He is described as six-feet tall,
medium build...
(Mulder) It's a cerebral oedema.
A swelling of the brain.
A trauma not uncommon
with this kind of accident.
Except this isn't accidental. The cause,
as it was stated to me, is self-inflicted.
There's a small hole in the skull
which allows oxygen into the brain cavity.
The reverend has three times the normal
blood volume pumping through his brain.
- And he did this himself?
- Yeah.
He probably did it when
he first got into prison.
- When he learned how to use its powers.
- Its powers?
There's a theory that at this point
in human evolution
our mental capabilities are limited
by inadequate blood supply.
Centuries ago, in the Peruvian Andes, holy
men used to remove parts of their skulls
to increase blood volume.
Or drill small holes.
This hole in his head enables Reverend
Orison to help these prisoners escape?
The practitioners of this found that
they could perform certain mental tricks.
One of which they called
"stopping the world".
Nobody can do that. I don't care
how many holes they have.
But maybe they can alter perception,
creating a disparate reality
which they project through hypnosis.
But, why? I mean, even if he could, why?
Donnie is serving a life sentence,
without possibility of parole.
That's the final judgment of society.
But not in the eyes of God. Or in the eyes
of a man who thinks he's God's tool.
Well, if Reverend Orison meant to kill
Donnie Pf aster, then why is he still alive?
Maybe he unleashed something
he couldn't control.
Maybe he thought he was
opening the door of perception,
but then, unwittingly, he...
opened the gates of hell.
(beeping)
- What?
- Glory. Amen.
Glory. Amen.
(beeping slows)
(knock at door)
- Are you Donald?
- Yes.
I'm from Tip Top Gentlemen's Service.
- This isn't your place, is it?
- No. Why?
Cos I was coming up and got stopped by
the landlord, like it's any of his business.
He told me some
Reverend Orison lives here.
- Now, you ain't no preacher, are you?
- No.
Good. They always like the weirdest things.
You know what I mean?
- You OK?
- Yes.
Something you want to say?
Love your hair.
What are you doin'?
- Is your hair chemically treated?
- My hair?
- I don't know which product to use.
- No, you're not using no product.
My hair's clean. If you're gonna
be weird about it, I ought to leave.
I'm being a gentleman.
Well, be a gentleman and get me a towel.
I'm gonna get outta here.
It's a wig.
They lied to me.
You lied to me!
Where did he go?
Marshal?
- Marshal?
- What?
The prisoner. The man you were guarding.
What happened to him?
He's gone, Scully. So's the marshal's gun.
You didn't see him?
Let's go, Scully.
- What is it?
- What does this mean?
- Did you tell him?
- No, I only told you.
He must have... overheard us
when we were talking in the hallway.
- I didn't mention the name of the song.
- You did.
No, I'm sure I didn't, Mulder.
Well... maybe this was meant for you.
"Don't look any further."
(cocks gun)
"Whosoever sheddeth man's blood...
by man shall his blood be shed."
- What are you doing?
- Taking you home.
The wicked... will be punished.
Pray for God's love, Donnie.
Find the humility in yourself
to allow God into your heart.
All you have to do is believe.
Repent. You'll feel God's love come to show
you the way to his heavenly kingdom.
(whimpers)
- Are you sorry for what you've done?
- You... (mumbles)
- What did you say?
- Never... no... no...
- Why are you crying?
- I can't... I can't... (mumbles)
Beg his forgiveness for what you did.
For what you did to all
those poor, helpless girls.
My violence is always waiting...
for an instant.
For when his back is turned.
You can see it now.
Are you crying for your sins?
Or for yourself?
No, Reverend. I cry for you...
because you cannot kill me.
You know, it's funny, when
all is said and done, there's...
not much mystery in murder.
And for that I owe you an apology, Mulder.
What do you mean?
Well, you were right. I was looking too hard
for connections that weren't there.
Orison was a murderer, plain and simple.
He liberated prisoners so he could
bring them here, pass judgment.
I guess in his own twisted way
he was making good with his god.
"Glory. Amen." Let's go home, Scully.
You know, Donnie Pf aster placed the call
to the police that led us out here.
It's like he's begging us to hunt him down.
This X-file is over... lying dead there
in a grave he dug himself.
Let's let the US Marshals
take over from here.
Don't look any further, Scully.
(phone rings)
- Fox Mulder. Leave a message after the...
- (beep)
Agent Mulder,
Marshal Joe Daddo in Marion.
Just talked to a call girl
who lD'd Donnie as an attacker.
Claims Pf aster got upset
when she was wearing a red wig.
Upset she wasn't a redhead. This mean
anything to you? Appreciate a call back.
(yells)
Go back to hell!
- Who does your nails, girly girl?
- Let me go!
The only reason you're alive
is because I asked the judge for life!
The only reason is because
we didn't kill you when we could!
You're the one that got away.
- You're all I think about.
- I'm a federal agent.
You do anything to me and they
will not give you a break this time.
I'm going to run you a bath.
(screams)
("Don't Look Any Further")
(turns radio off)
(turns radio on)
("Don't Look Any Further" by John Hiatt)
Now be good, and don't
cause me any problems.
(water running)
(phone ringing)
(continues ringing)
("Don't Look Any Further"
by John Hiatt)
(ringing tone)
(turns stereo off)
(mouthing) Put 'em up!
(mouthing) Did he hurt you?
(door opens)
- Excuse me.
- (cop) Yeah. Sure.
If you want to pack some things,
we can get out of here.
Yeah.
You can't judge yourself.
- Maybe I don't have to.
- The Bible allows for vengeance.
But the law doesn't.
The way I see it...
he didn't give you a choice.
And my report will reflect that...
in case you're worried.
Donnie Pf aster would have surely
killed again if given the chance.
He was evil, Mulder.
I'm sure about that without a doubt.
But there's one thing that I'm not sure of.
- What's that?
- Who was at work in me?
Or what?
What made me...
What made me pull the trigger?
You mean, if it was God?
I mean... what if it wasn't?
Visiontext Subtitles: Yasmin Rammohan
(Child) I made this!