(woman) We're so sorry, Becky.
If there's anything we can do for you,
anything at all, just let us know.
(Becky) Thank you so much.
It would have meant a lot to him.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you for coming.
Mrs Crouch,
I'm sorry for your loss.
Thank you, Mr...?
Johnson.
I worked briefly with your husband.
I was impressed by him.
Very much so.
Thank you.
Sorry.
Hell of a Christmas, Raymond.
He's at peace now.
That's one small comfort to be drawn.
Didn't even leave a note.
I am the resurrection and the life. He
that believeth in Me, though he were dead,
yet shall he live.
Whosoever liveth and
believeth in Me shall never die.
(continues reciting verse)
He that believeth in Me,
though he were dead,
yet shall he live.
(phone rings)
Thank you, ma'am.
- Are you with the FBI too?
- Yes, sir.
Look, I know my job.
The man was deceased.
- I'm sorry?
- I understand that he was one of your own.
But these rumours I'm hearing that I put
a living human being into the ground...
You people better get
your facts straight, real fast.
Mulder? You been spreading rumours?
Why? Hear any good ones lately?
Not particularly.
So what do you have here?
- Merry Christmas, by the way, Scully.
- Thank you. Merry Christmas to you too.
Grave robbery with a twist.
Check out the head liner, Scully.
Well, it looks like someone
on the inside was trying to get out.
Indeed it does. To answer you,
I haven't been spreading any rumours.
The local PD's been doing
a pretty good job of that,
ever since they matched
the fingerprints on the dead man to these.
And to those up there on that headstone.
There's a big, juicy handprint on the back.
What about the person or persons
who did the digging?
Well, we got one pile of dirt.
I'm guessing one man with a shovel.
Other than that, last night's rain
hasn't left us much to go on.
Well, go ahead, Scully, nay-say me.
The body of a FBI agent gets disinterred,
only to climb out on its own
and disappear into the Yuletide night.
- See, you had me up until there.
- Did I?
I think it's what you said before.
I think it's a grave robbery with a twist.
You've got the fingerprints
and the torn casket liner.
Most likely it's rigged evidence that's
been faked by whoever exhumed the body.
- Faked for what effect?
- Publicity?
Fear? Rumours?
I mean, I don't know what specific effect,
but nonetheless, it's...
- What?
- Looks like blood.
(recites the resurrection verse very fast)
(banging)
(recites the resurrection verse)
Special Agent Raymond Crouch.
Age 56, married, no children.
After a sterling 21-year career
with the Bureau, he retired in 1993.
Then, earlier this month,
he was found in the garage of his
Tallahassee home, service weapon in hand.
- Definitely self-inflicted?
- I read over the report
and there's no indication otherwise.
How about a motive
for the grave robberies?
We've gone through Crouch's cases.
He doesn't seem to have made any enemies.
Same thing with his personal life.
No large debts, no feuds with neighbours,
never a bad word against him.
- Nothing stands out?
- Should something stand out?
Agent Mulder, what's your take on this?
Only that I don't think
it was grave robbery per se.
It was necromancy.
The summoning of the dead.
It's magic, dating back to shamanism,
with a long tradition in the Christian church.
The dead are brought back to life to divulge
arcane knowledge and perform ritual tasks.
So this wacko thought
he was raising the dead?
That's what he was doin'. This is a...
That's a magic circle drawn in goat's blood.
The rain washed most of it away.
The blood attracts the undead, while
the circle focuses the necromancer's power,
while protecting him
from the spirits that he's conjuring.
OK.
He may also desire to wear
the clothes of the dead man
to create a bond between them.
You would not want to be
this man's dry-cleaner.
Obviously, there are
clear ritualistic elements to this crime.
But the question is, why were they
directed at Raymond Crouch?
That is the question.
Well, let's come up with an answer.
Mulder, Scully, a word, please?
Necromancy aside,
this magic circle you mentioned,
what if it looked something like this?
It's an Ouroboros, possibly.
Definitely a mystical symbol.
The alchemists favoured it. They believed
that it represented all of existence.
I'm thinking more the Millennium Group.
It was their symbol as well.
- Are you familiar with them?
- Somewhat. They were former FBI agents
who offered consulting services
to law enforcement.
- Somehow, they fell into disrepute.
- They operated in extreme secrecy.
They had their own agenda, which was less
than altruistic, if not improper or illegal.
And that it was, in fact, a cult based upon
Judaeo-Christian end-time prophecies
concerning the coming millennium.
- Was Raymond Crouch a member?
- I can't seem to find out.
The group dissolved several months ago.
They left no paper trail, nothing.
However, I do have three other grave
desecrations all within the last six months.
Long Island, Northern California, Arizona.
All three graves contained
the bodies of former FBI agents.
All three were recent suicides.
How long were you going to sit on this?
Owing to the Millennium Group's
former ties with the Bureau,
this matter is sensitive, to say the least.
- Investigate them. Keep a low profile.
- I think I know where to start.
- How well do you know this man?
- Only by reputation.
He left VICAP before I got there.
But he's been called the greatest criminal
profiler the Quantico ever produced.
- What's he doing here?
- Good morning.
Apparently, he checked himself in
for a 30-day observation.
I gather the last few years
haven't been kind to him.
He can tell us about the Millennium Group.
He used to consult for 'em.
Later, he fought to bring them down
at the expense of his own career.
Single-minded.
Sounds like someone I know.
(TV) ..12-yard line. They are threatening.
Frank Black?
My name is Fox Mulder.
This is my partner, Dana Scully.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Do you mind if we sit down?
- Who's playing?
- It's Notre Dame and Boston College.
Ah, the Fighting Irish
and the Golden Eagles, huh?
What can I do for you, agents?
We're working on a case that we feel
you might have some particular insight into.
The death of four FBI agents.
Do you recognise these men?
I do.
All four committed suicide
in the last six months.
All were exhumed from their graves
in a ritual desecration.
They were members of
the Millennium Group, is that correct?
Sir, we've been having a really difficult time
gleaning any information about the group.
About its membership, its practices.
- I believe you can help us.
- No, thank you.
I'm retired.
I think you can tell that
I'm trying to put my life back together.
- I can't get involved in this.
- We're not asking you to.
I'm asking you to take a look at the case file.
No, thank you.
Mr Black, the day after tomorrow
is January 1st, 2000.
That's the significant date for these people.
That doesn't leave us much time.
Don't you want to see them stopped?
Well, Mr Black,
you are not what I was expecting.
- Agent Mulder.
- Yes.
It's 1st & 18. Just let me
watch this game in peace.
- It's 3rd & 10. Notre Dame.
- Happy New Year.
Same to you.
- Evenin'.
- Hi.
Could I give you a hand?
Oh, no. I'm about done. But thanks.
- Guess I ran over a nail or somethin'.
- Well, I can help you see at least.
Well, I've been drivin' all night.
Be good to get home.
Ihearya.
(sniffs the air) Man, whew!
What is that?
I think a deer, maybe,
must have died out there in the woods.
(flies buzzing)
Sir.
What's in the truck?
- Nothing.
- Mind if I take a look?
- There's nothing in there, so...
- Drop that. Take two steps back.
Drop it.
(buzzing)
(recites resurrection verse)
Stand up, there. Stand up!
Let me see your hands!
- (recites verse)
- What?
Speak up!
(screaming)
Hey.
I have the men concentrating on the woods.
Our necromancer was definitely here.
It's salt. Heavy magic.
If you're gonna tell me that he stopped
by the side of the road to raise the dead -
which I hope you're not-
I've got two things to say to you.
One is that his previous circles
were made of blood, not salt, and two...
They were large enough for a body.
This is a protective circle
for one man to stand in.
- Protecting himself against what?
- Whatever it was that did that.
Agents!
Over here!
I saw a lump in the ground.
My God.
Bite marks. They look human.
More salt.
"I am he that liveth and was dead; and,
behold, I am alive for evermore, Amen;
and have the keys of hell and of death."
Book of Revelation. Chapter one, verse 18.
Go, Fighting Irish.
1st&18.
It's not football, it's Revelations.
You wanted to tell us something.
Why not just come out and say it?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I cannot get involved in this.
All right, so you'll occasionally
drop a little arcane hint?
A police officer was murdered, Frank.
Why do you want to play around?
Your denials aside,
you know something about that.
You knew that we'd find this.
What are you afraid of?
Losing your daughter.
You're in a custody battle
with the parents of your late wife.
I just spoke with your doctor.
That's why you're here.
They claimed I was an unfit father, obsessed
with conspiracy and the end of the world.
That my work meant more to me
than my daughter, Jordan.
The thing is, they were right.
And so you retired.
I will sell insurance. I'll do whatever it takes.
I'll get well and I'll jump through hoops,
but I will not mention
the Millennium Group again.
But you obviously wanna help.
You dropped that clue on us.
Look, Frank, nobody
needs to know about this.
We're just three people
sittin' around talking.
The Book of Revelation describes
the end of the physical world
in a battle between heaven and hell,
good against evil.
The Millennium Group believed
that that time was upon us.
These four represent a schism in the group.
They believe that for the end time to come,
man must take an active hand
in bringing that about.
- And to that end they committed suicide?
- Yeah.
With the express purpose
of being brought back to life.
The four horsemen of the Apocalypse.
These four men bring with them
war, pestilence, famine and death.
So that all the dead of the earth will rise.
Armageddon.
It must begin with the dawn
of the Millennium or not at all.
That's what they believe.
The man you're looking for,
your necromancer,
he exhumed these men
in accordance with their wishes.
Is he a member of the Millennium Group?
No, they sought him out. He believes
he's doing God's work, but he's mistaken.
Could you tell us a bit more about this man?
He's a white male, 45 to 50.
He's a religious man. No police record.
No fulfilling relationship.
You would pass him
without giving him a glance.
So this is the one event
that will give his life meaning?
Yeah. He needs privacy for this.
He'll live alone.
Possibly in the house he grew up in.
Most likely, it's a large, rural property,
away from prying eyes.
He'll own a truck or a van.
He needs it to transport the bodies.
There'll be high fences.
"No Trespassing" signs.
It's a solitary existence.
He's worked around death
all his life, in some capacity.
A funeral parlour or a cemetery.
Death comforts him.
He took great care in burying the deputy,
in preparing the body,
despite the fact that he feared being caught.
He stapled the lips, sealed the mouth shut.
It was to prevent the man from coming back
to life. He believes that, if disturbed,
the deputy will rise from the dead.
It's too soon for that.
So when he realises
the deputy has been discovered,
he'll feel a need to take action.
He'll return to the body first chance he gets.
Rice County Morgue.
I think you'll catch him there.
These four members
of the Millennium Group,
the ones that truly liveth, who were dead,
these are the ones we have to catch.
Mr Black. You've got a phone call.
I think it might be your daughter.
Thank you. My daughter. Excuse me.
It's more important to track down
four dead bodies than one murderer?
He's not our murderer.
And those four bodies aren't dead.
- And the millennium is 14 hours away.
- These people, even when they were alive,
mangled biblical prophecy
to the extent that it's unrecognisable.
Our year 2000
is just their artificial deadline.
And besides, 2001 is actually
the start of the new millennium.
Nobody likes a math geek, Scully.
Anyway, I think that
Frank's profile is sound.
And I think with it we have the best chance
of finding this necromancer, as you call him.
- So I am going down to the county morgue.
- I absolutely think you should.
- And what are you gonna do?
- Follow the profile.
The deputy was killed on a road
that connects with no major highway.
I think our necromancer lives nearby.
I'll do a rundown on
all single landowners in the area.
See where the bodies are buried, since we...
Oh, Scully, would you do me a favour?
Don't let anyone remove the staples
from the deputy's mouth.
Please, just humour me. Thanks.
Proceeding with the visual
examination of the mouth.
(phone rings)
Jesus.
What appears to be salt
is packed into the victim's mouth.
God only knows why.
Am removing it.
(phone rings)
This is Agent Dana Scully with the FBI.
Please do not autopsy the murder victim
that was brought in earlier.
The sheriff's deputy.
If you've already started, stop now.
I'll be there shortly,
and I'll explain when I arrive.
(screams)
Hello?
(phone signal)
Where is she?
Sir?
How you feelin'?
- All things considered?
- What the hell happened here?
- Who is that man?
- The sheriff's deputy.
The man we found this morning.
He was dead.
And then, somehow, he wasn't.
He attacked me.
You shot him?
Three rounds, centre of mass into his chest.
No effect.
There's a gunshot wound
to his head as well.
Yeah, this man
Mulder calls the necromancer,
our suspect, he was here too.
He fired that shot with my gun.
He saved me. I have no idea why.
He got away,
but I was in no shape to follow.
Look, sir, I can't even begin to offer
an explanation for what happened.
But I have to say
it is exactly what Mulder feared.
Yeah, which is why I would like to talk to
him. Why isn't he answering his phone?
Well, welcome to the boondocks.
(sings)
Hey! Open the door! Open the door!
Open up! Let me out! Hey!
(gunshots)
I haven't heard from him.
He didn't go to the morgue with you?
No, he went looking for our suspect's home.
No one's been able to contact him since.
I've got task-force agents canvassing
the northwestern Maryland area,
but it's a large territory to cover
and we're running out of time.
Sir, I'm just afraid that Mulder
may have found what he's looking for.
- I need your help in finding him.
- You respected my reasons in the past.
- Please respect 'em now.
- I'm not sure I understand your reasons, sir.
And I'm starting to wonder what this is
all about and how much you know about it.
Mulder mentioned the four Millennium
members "who liveth" and were dead.
Now, this morning,
I saw what he was talking about.
You did?
- One of them attacked me.
- I'm sorry.
Now, as crazy as this sounds, I have to ask.
Do you believe that the Millennium Group
is capable of bringing about the end time?
Armageddon?
I understand their beliefs.
I've spent years trying to unravel them.
Make sense of them.
Doesn't mean I believe them myself.
But what if it were true?
Good and evil, which would prevail?
I'm sorry.
Octavia. I'm gonna check myself out.
- You'd like a day pass?
- I won't be coming back.
(growling)
(twig breaks)
Who's there?
- It's me.
- You came.
I almost didn't.
We'd given up on ya. Thank God.
Thank God.
There's someone in the basement.
Policeman.
He killed one of the members.
He shot him in the head.
But you're here.
Now we'll have four.
I'm here.
I can't tell you how happy I am.
You were meant to be the fourth.
I always knew that.
- I so hoped you'd come around.
- I didn't want to.
The man in the basement-
I told him how to find this place.
You... Why?
I was trying to walk
the straight and narrow.
Leave the Millennium Group behind.
But I know that I can't do that any more.
Now that I know you've succeeded.
- You didn't believe the dead would arise.
- No.
You see what the future holds, Frank.
- You know you can't run from it.
- No, I can't run.
You've paid so dearly.
They've taken your daughter from you.
Murdered your wife.
There is no justice in this world.
But there will be in the next.
The hour is near.
Are you ready, Frank?
I'm ready.
I am the resurrection and the life.
He that believeth in Me,
- though he were dead...
- Yet shall he live.
Whosoever liveth and believeth
in Me shall never die.
(Phone)
- Scully.
- This is Skinner.
We back-checked Frank Black, as you asked.
- And?
- He took no calls, except from his daughter.
But the staff took messages
from a Rice County number.
That's where I am.
We ran phone records
for the desecration victims.
All four received calls
from this number before their deaths.
I'm gonna need an address.
I'm begging you, please. You know
what the world is. Evil goes unpunished.
The good suffer. There's no future here
but uncertainty and pain.
Let the judgment come.
You're damning yourself, Frank!
Agent Mulder?
Can you hear me?
- Agent Mulder?
- Yeah. I'm down here.
They're all around.
- You armed?
- Oh, yeah.
Shoot for the head. That seems to stop 'em.
- There's three of 'em.
- Where?
I don't know. They're hiding.
- Mulder, can you get up?
- I think so.
Look out!
(growling)
(gun clicks)
(TV) There's another shot
of that millennium crystal ball,
and they're gettin' ready to bring in
the new year. They are packed in tonight.
Body heat alone is keeping 'em warm. And
look at it - all the way up past 52nd Street.
That is that X-shaped thing I was
talkin' about before. This is Times Square.
- Mr Black.
- Hi.
Mark Johnson's been taken
for a psychiatric evaluation.
He'll be put under suicide watch,
just as you asked.
- Good.
- And, um...
- What?
- There's someone here to see you.
- Hi, Daddy!
- Hiya, little one.
- Well. Oh, I missed you, sweetheart.
- I missed you too, Daddy.
Let's get outta here.
Frank, good luck with everything.
Agent Mulder, Agent Scully.
I guess this is it.
You're not gonna stay and watch?
We just wanna go home.
Take care of yourselves.
Hug your friends and loved ones tight,
what the heck, whoever that person is
next to you. No time like the present.
Here we go. Ten, nine, eight,
seven, six, five,
four, three, two...
Happy new year 2000.
(crowd sings "Auld Lang Syne")
- The world didn't end.
- No, it didn't.
- Happy new year, Scully.
- Happy new year, Mulder.
Visiontext Subtitles:
Marisa Castle de Joncaire
(Child) I made this!