DUSTIN: [ On radio ]
Fred. Fred, do you copy?
-BRING HIM UP.
-QUICK, BRING HIM UP!
GET HIM OUT OF THERE.
GET HIM OUT OF THERE. HURRY.
HELP HIM OUT OF HERE.
GOT TO GET FRED TO SOME HEAT.
HE'S CHILLED.
WELL, I GOT
THE HEAT ROOM GOING.
GO UP THERE AND GET
IN THAT HOT ROOM.
YEAH. I GOT YOU.
YEAH. I'M JUST SHAKING.
MY WHOLE BODY
IS SHAKING RIGHT NOW.
♪♪
BUT IT DON'T TAKE LONG,
WHEN YOU'RE COLD,
TO GET HYPOTHERMIA.
I MEAN, WHEN YOU'RE
SHAKING INSIDE, YOU KNOW
IT AIN'T JUST 'CAUSE YOU'RE
[BLEEP] ABOUT BEING COLD.
IT IS COLD.
♪♪
HEY, FRED, YOU GOT
TO PRESS THE BUTTON!
-WHAT'S HE YELLING?
-HE SAYS, "PUSH THE BUTTON."
-THE BUTTON!
-I [BLEEP] KNOW HOW TO DO THIS,
[BLEEP]
OH, I'M MESSING WITH FRED.
I CAN'T HELP IT.
HEY, DUSTIN,
STOP GOOFING OFF!
♪♪
I AM GOING INTO THE MOUTH
OF THE DRAGON TODAY, BROTHER.
THAT'S WHERE THE GOLD'S AT, MAN.
I NEED YOU TO GO FARTHER
THAN WE'VE GONE.
-CARLOS!
-HE'S DROWNING.
GET HIM OUT OF THERE.
HURRY.
MAN:
Diver coming up.
-THERE IS GOLD IN HERE.
-WHAT?
-THERE IS GOLD.
-IT'S GOLD!
[BLEEP] YEAH, IT'S GOLD.
DAMN RIGHT IT'S GOLD.
HE'S GOT THE FEVER!
WHOO! SEE WHAT I'M DOING RIGHT?
THAT'S [BLEEP] UP, BRO.
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
DISCOVERY COMMUNICATIONS
♪♪
EXACTLY.
Narrator:
THE DAKOTA BOYS ARE DREDGING
IN ONE OF ALASKA'S MOST REMOTE
AND TREACHEROUS CREEKS.
♪♪
WHOO!
THEY'RE SEARCHING FOR A GOLD
DEPOSIT ON THE BEDROCK SO BIG
IT WILL MAKE THEM ALL
MILLIONAIRES.
FRED, TELL THEM
TO FIND ME SOME GOLD!
YEAH! DO IT!
♪♪
WHAT HAPPENED?
WAIT. WHOA, WHOA. [BLEEP]
WE GOT TO SHUT IT DOWN.
SLOW IT DOWN.
IDLE DOWN.
♪♪
I JUST WANT EVERYTHING
TO WORK RIGHT NOW.
♪♪
AH [BLEEP]
MESSING UP MY DAY.
SHUTTING DOWN.
♪♪
FRED:
Diver's coming up!
♪♪
NICE AND EASY.
WE'RE OUT THERE
BUSTING OUR BUNS,
BUT WE'RE NOT DOING WELL AT ALL.
THIS HAS BEEN A ROTTEN WEEK.
♪♪
Dustin:
I FEEL LIKE I'M WASTING MY TIME.
I MEAN, THERE COULD BE GOLD
WHERE I'M DIGGING RIGHT NOW,
BUT WE HAVEN'T SEEN IT YET.
Narrator: THE CREW IS ALL
ON A SHARE OF THE PROFITS.
BUT BEFORE ANY OF THEM
MAKE A DIME,
THEY HAVE TO REPAY THEIR
INVESTOR THEIR RUNNING COSTS,
$50,000.
I'M AFRAID THAT,
IF WE DON'T HAVE
A SUBSTANTIAL AMOUNT OF GOLD
IN A COUPLE OF WEEKS,
WE'RE IN BIG TROUBLE.
Dustin: HOLY [BLEEP]
Narrator: SIX WEEKS AGO,
DUSTIN DISCOVERED
HIS LARGEST-EVER NUGGET.
I'LL BE DAMNED.
WE FOUND NUGGETS.
THAT'S BIGGER THAN WE EVER
GOT FROM PORCUPINE CREEK.
IT'S ONLY GOING TO GET BIGGER.
COME ON!
THEY BUILT A DIVERSION
TO PROTECT THEM
FROM THE 2,000 GALLONS OF WATER
CRASHING DOWN THE RAVINE
EVERY SECOND
AND MINED A DIVE CREW
DOWNSTREAM FROM DUSTIN'S FIND.
♪♪
MAN: Whoo-hoo!
These rocks are coming loose!
Oh, I'm digging now.
♪♪
Narrator: BUT WITH MOST
OF THE SEASON OVER,
THEY'VE FOUND LESS THAN
$1,000 WORTH OF GOLD.
♪♪
Dustin: THIS IS SAD.
WE'RE MORE THAN HALFWAY
THROUGH THE SEASON, GUYS,
AND THIS ISN'T LOOKING GOOD.
THIS ISN'T ENOUGH.
THIS DOESN'T EVEN PAY
FOR ONE 55-GALLON DRUM OF FUEL.
Narrator: THE DAKOTA BOYS ARE
STARING FAILURE IN THE FACE.
♪♪
WE KNOW THIS NUGGET RIGHT HERE,
THAT ONE,
CAME FROM UPSTREAM A LITTLE BIT.
Fred: WELL, WHAT WE
GOING TO DO ABOUT IT?
WE ARE GOING TO MOVE
THE DIVERSION UPSTREAM,
RIGHT UNDERNEATH THE BRIDGE,
RIGHT WHERE I FOUND THE NUGGET.
THAT'S WHERE THE GOLD'S AT.
WE'RE GOING TO THE GOLD.
I HAVE ONLY ONE PIECE OF ADVICE.
IN MY OPINION, YOU'D BE WASTING
YOUR TIME IF YOU GO UPSTREAM.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
THAT NUGGET WAS A FLUKE
IN THE SURFACE UP THERE.
WELL, WITH THAT NUGGET
SITTING THERE LIKE THAT,
THERE HAS GOT TO BE
SOME OTHER ONES THAT HEAVY
SITTING RIGHT BY IT.
SO WHAT I NEED IS A WHOLE
BUNCH OF DOUBT RIGHT NOW.
♪♪
I'M JUST SAYING.
THIS IS MY ADVICE.
♪♪
I THINK THERE'S
GOLD UP THERE.
I THINK THERE'S PLENTY
OF GOLD UP THERE.
WRONG OR RIGHT,
WE'RE DOING IT.
THAT'S IT.
♪♪
Dustin: THIS HAS TO GET DONE.
I NEED SOME GOLD.
THERE'S NO MORE ARGUING ANYMORE.
WE'RE DOING IT MY WAY.
♪♪
WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO IS WE'RE
GOING TO TAKE THIS DIVERSION
AND STICK IT UP THERE,
UP-CREEK,
TO WHERE WE CAN DIVE RIGHT THERE
AND ROCK WON'T BREAK US.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS.
NOW, MY FIRST INSTINCT IS
JUST TO PICK THE DAMN THING UP
AND WALK AROUND WITH IT.
BUT FIRST THING I NEED TO DO,
TAKE THE PLYWOOD OFF.
WE'RE GOING TO TRY
TO GET BOARDS UP.
JUST HOPEFULLY
IT'S LIGHT ENOUGH,
WE CAN MOVE THE DAMN THING.
Narrator: DUSTIN'S PLAN --
REMOVE THE BOARDS
AND MOVE THE BEAM
15 FEET UPSTREAM,
ANCHOR IT AND SECURE IT
WITH CABLES,
THEN REINSERT THE BOARDS
TO CREATE A SAFE DIVING AREA
IN THE SPOT WHERE DUSTIN
FOUND HIS NUGGET.
♪♪
Dustin:
WHOO! THIS IS CRAZY.
-ARE YOU EXCITED, MAN?
-YEAH, MAN.
THIS IS GOLD.
THERE IT GOES. IT'S TILTED.
AND OUT.
♪♪
-LET IT GO.
-SEE YOU, BOARDS!
-BE CAREFUL, MAN.
-I GOT THIS ONE. GO GET --
BYE!
Fred: OH, LOOK AT THAT.
WHAT THE HELL DID THEY DO THERE?
JUST LETTING THE DAMN BOARDS GO.
OKAY. I GOT IT. I GOT IT.
THROW THE BOARDS
INTO A RAGING CREEK
AND THINK THEY'RE GOING
TO JUST STAY THERE?
COME ON, NOW.
THINK OF WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
I GOT ANOTHER ONE FOR YOU.
ALL RIGHT. FINALLY,
WE GOT A SYSTEM GOING.
LOOK A LITTLE AMATEURISH,
BUT GOT A SYSTEM GOING FINALLY.
[ LAUGHS ]
♪♪
ABOUT THE FIRST THREE
OR FOUR OF THOSE
ARE REAL HARD TO PULL OUT
OF THERE, BECAUSE IT'S TIGHT.
WE CAN'T LIFT IT
WITH THEM IN THERE.
WHEW! I DON'T KNOW IF THEY'RE
GOING TO COME OUT, FRED.
WE MIGHT HAVE
TO CUT THEM OFF.
-[BLEEP]
-YEAH. THEY SWELLED UP GOOD.
YEAH. THEY FIT.
THIS RATE,
WE'LL GET NOWHERE.
MAYBE WE JUST LEAVE
THE DAMN THINGS IN
AND SEE HOW FAR
WE CAN GET WITH THAT?
I WAS JUST GOING
TO MUSCLE IT UP,
BUT NOW WITH THE ADDED
WEIGHT OF THE LUMBER,
IT'S PROBABLY 500 POUNDS PLUS,
AND IT'S HARD TO WALK AROUND
IN WHITE WATER WITH 500 POUNDS.
♪♪
SOMEBODY IS GOING TO HAVE
TO HELP ME LIFT IT, I THINK.
♪♪
Fred: HOW ABOUT --
HERE'S MY SUGGESTION.
TIE ONE COME-ALONG OFF
ON THE BRIDGE,
THEN TIE ANOTHER ONE HERE
AND GO FARTHER OUT WITH IT
AND CRANK BOTH OF THEM
AND JUST KIND OF WALK IT ALONG
LIKE THAT.
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
Narrator: FRED'S NEW PLAN --
USE A COME-ALONG TO WINCH
THE 500-POUND DIVERSION
UPSTREAM TO AN ANCHOR POINT,
THEN USE A SECOND CABLE
ATTACHED TO THE BRIDGE
TO SWING THE BEAM UP
AND INTO POSITION.
♪♪
WE'LL SEE HOW THIS GOES.
IT LOOKS LIKE A NIGHTMARE.
Fred: CARLOS!
VERY CAREFULLY...
-ALL RIGHT.
-...PRY THE BOTTOM AWAY.
BE PREPARED FOR IT TO FALL OVER.
I GOTCHA.
Dustin: SO, REMEMBER, WHEN THAT
THING GOES, IT'S GOING TO GO.
THAT'S IT.
LOOK OUT!
HOLY CRAP.
I KNOW. I KNOW. I KNOW.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S ALL RIGHT. IT'S ALL RIGHT.
-GO! WHOO-HOO-HOO!
-GREAT JOB! YEAH!
-ALL RIGHT. COME ON.
-THERE YOU GO.
-IT'S GOING NOW.
-COME-ALONG!
KEEP IT UP.
[ MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY ]
OH [BLEEP]
HANG ON TO YOUR CABLE!
♪♪
Narrator: WES WINCHES THE BEAM
AGAINST ALMOST 500 TONS
OF WHITE WATER PER MINUTE.
♪♪
Dustin: STOP! STOP! STOP! STOP!
THE HOOK'S OFF.
STOP! STOP! STOP!
HOOK'S OFF.
JUST HOOK IT.
I DON'T GIVE A [BLEEP] WHERE.
♪♪
AH, WE'RE FIGURING IT OUT.
IT'S A MADHOUSE, THOUGH.
WE'RE OBVIOUSLY [LAUGHS]
DOING IT '50s GHETTO STYLE.
GOD.
THIS IS INSANE.
WE'RE CRAZY, DUDE.
JUST SORT OF HANGING
ON THAT ROCK.
YEAH. JUST WALK OUT THERE,
CRAZY MOTHER[BLEEP]
OH, MY [BLEEP]
Carlos: [BLEEP] YEAH, MAN.
DON'T STOP HIM!
-GO FOR BROKE, DUDE.
-WHOO!
-YEAH, THAT'S WORKING EXCELLENT.
♪♪
Fred:
GOT ABOUT 18 INCHES.
WE'RE ALMOST THERE, FRED.
GIVE ME ONE MORE SECOND.
ALL RIGHT. YOU'RE GOOD
WHERE YOU'RE AT, RIGHT?
ALL RIGHT.
GRAB AHOLD TO THIS THING,
AND DON'T YOU DARE
LET IT GO.
GOOD JOB!
♪♪
Narrator: UP AHEAD...
YOU GOT GOLD, BY THE WAY.
-WHAT?!
-THERE IS GOLD.
IT'S GOLD! [BLEEP] YEAH, IT'S
GOLD! DAMN RIGHT, IT'S GOLD!
HE'S GOT THE FEVER!
SEE WHAT I'M DOING RIGHT?
THAT'S [BLEEP] UP, BRO.
♪♪
-ALL RIGHT.
-THAT'S STAGE ONE.
Dustin: MY GOAL IS TO GET THIS
BUTTED UP AGAINST THAT ROCK
RIGHT THERE,
TIGHT AS IT WILL GO.
Narrator:
THE DAKOTA BOYS ARE SHIFTING
THEIR DIVERSION BEAM UPSTREAM
TO CREATE A SAFE DIVING AREA
WHERE DUSTIN BELIEVES THERE'S
A MASSIVE DEPOSIT OF GOLD.
♪♪
Carlos: WE'RE GOING
MORE EXTREME THIS TIME.
WE'RE GOING TO MOVE IT UP
TO RIGHT ABOUT THERE,
WHERE THE MOST HEAVY
PART OF THE CREEK IS,
SO THAT'S GOING TO PUT,
LIKE, SOME CRAZY FORCE
ON THIS DIVERSION.
THEY HAVE ONE END OF
THE DIVERSION BEAM FIXED.
NOW FOR THE HARD PART --
WINCH THE OTHER END
OUT INTO THE CURRENT,
WHERE THEY'LL ANCHOR IT
IN THE CENTER OF THE CREEK.
Fred:
EVERYTHING'S CLEAR.
Dustin:
PICK IT UP, FRED!
YOU READY?
GOOD.
DAMN. THAT THING IS NOT --
HEY, FRED,
YOU GOT TO PRESS THE BUTTON!
-TELL HIM WAIT A MINUTE.
-THERE'S A BUTTON! YOU PRESS IT!
-WHAT'S HE YELLING?
-HE SAYS, "PUSH THE BUTTON."
PRESS THE BUTTON DOWN!
THERE'S A LEVER.
YEAH. IT DIDN'T WORK.
JUST LIKE --
YOU'RE GETTING --
I [BLEEP] KNOW HOW TO DO THIS,
SON OF A [BLEEP]
HOLD IT WITH, UH --
ALMOST!
YOU KNOW, COOPER, SOMETIMES
YOU'RE A PAIN IN THE ASS!
OH, I'M MESSING WITH FRED.
I CAN'T HELP IT.
OH, WHAT THE...
'CAUSE I KNOW
HE KNOWS HOW TO USE THAT TOOL,
AND HE KNOWS I KNOW
HOW TO USE THAT TOOL,
BUT HE JUST KEEPS GOING,
SO I GIVE HIM
A HARD TIME WHEN I CAN.
YOU PULL ON THE LEVER!
IF YOU DO IT AT THE SAME TIME,
IT'LL RELEASE!
DON'T NEED THAT BULL[BLEEP]
RIGHT NOW.
GET THAT, AND PUT IT UP.
I SEE WHAT IT IS.
THERE YOU GO!
♪♪
GO AHEAD. STAND IT UP.
-ALL RIGHT.
-RIGHT THERE.
♪♪
Man:
TRY TO KEEP THE SLACK OUT.
THIS WOULD BE PERFECT
RIGHT THERE.
-LET IT STAY SLACK.
-COME ON, NOW. GO DOWN THERE.
-CRANK ON IT A LITTLE BIT.
-THAT'S WORKING.
CRANK ON IT, CARLOS.
-THAT'S WORKING PRETTY GOOD.
-CRANK A LITTLE BIT MORE.
-HOLD UP.
-THAT'S GOOD. STOP. STOP.
AH, YOU'RE IN
A STRAIGHT LINE NOW.
STAND BY. ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE GOOD. WE'RE GOOD.
WE'RE GOOD. WE CAN SET IT NOW.
LOOKING GOOD.
COMING THROUGH
WAS COMING THROUGH, MAN.
COWBOY WAY, BROTHER.
COWBOY WAY.
[BLEEP] DANG.
♪♪
START PUTTING OUR LITTLE BOARDS
IN OUR DIVERSION HERE,
NICE AND VERTICAL,
ABOUT WHERE WE WANT IT.
NOW IT'S JUST
THE FIRST THREE OR FOUR
IS THE ONLY ONES
THAT REALLY NEED IT.
OH, MAN. I'M NEVER
DOING IT RIGHT, MAN.
I ASSUME, IF I'M MOVING,
I'M DOING IT WRONG.
Dustin:
PAUL, SLOW DOWN, MAN.
YOU'RE ON
ONE [BLEEP] ANCHOR HERE.
IT'S STARTING TO --
IT'S A LOT OF PRESSURE.
IT'S GOING TO SCOOT OVER
ON YOU IN A MINUTE.
IT FEELS PRETTY UNSTABLE.
IT COMES LOOSE,
YOU'RE GOING TO FOR A RIDE.
YEAH, NOT A PLEASANT ONE.
-[ LAUGHS ]
-[BLEEP] THAT.
♪♪
OH, THAT CURRENT
IS PICKING UP OVER HERE NOW.
WHOO!
♪♪
Narrator:
FIVE HOURS IN, THEY FINALLY
GET THE LAST BOARD IN PLACE.
♪♪
IT DOESN'T SEEM LIKE
IT'S SLOWING IT DOWN ANY.
THAT'S A LOT OF WATER, MAN.
MIGHT THINK ABOUT
PUTTING A STIFF BOARD
BETWEEN THERE AND THERE.
THAT'S NOT A BAD IDEA.
♪♪
I GOT YOUR PIZZA PIE!
[ LAUGHTER ]
Fred: HEY, DUSTIN.
STOP GOOFING OFF!
PASS ME THEM BOARDS UP THERE.
Dustin: YOU DON'T STOP
HOLLERING ORDERS AT ME,
I'M GOING TO FLIP OUT.
JUST GIVE ME THE BOARD.
♪♪
ALL RIGHT!
LET'S GET HER DONE!
LAST PIECE, BOYS!
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M GOING TO SEE
WHAT THEY CAN DO WITH IT.
KEEP GOING. KEEP GOING.
THERE IT GOES.
-THAT LOOKS BETTER.
-OH, YEAH. NOW --
-NOW WE'RE THERE!
-THAT'S LOOKING A LOT BETTER.
FOUND IT!
-IT'S WORKING.
-LOOK AT IT.
HELL, FRED,
EVEN YOU CAN SWIM IN THERE.
[ LAUGHS ]
♪♪
Dustin: TODAY STARTS A NEW GAME,
COMPLETELY NEW DIG.
WE'VE DONE ALL THE PREP WORK.
WE'RE GOING FOR IT NOW.
♪♪
Narrator:
DUSTIN'S NEW DIVERSION
HAS CREATED A PROTECTED AREA
TO DIVE
WHERE HE BELIEVES THERE'S
A MASSIVE DEPOSIT OF GOLD.
Dustin:
WE GOT THIS DIVERSION UP.
NOW ALL WE GOT TO DO
IS GET IN THERE,
JUST GO IN STRAIGHT
TO THE GOLD THIS TIME.
IT'S GOING TO WORK.
Narrator: 73-YEAR-OLD FRED
WITH HIS 10 YEARS
OF DIVING EXPERIENCE
IS PULLING RANK AND TAKES
THE FIRST DIVE IN THE NEW SITE.
♪♪
WE'RE GOING AFTER AN AREA THAT
NEVER GOT DREDGED BEFORE, EVER.
NOBODY'S EVER BEEN THERE,
AND WE'RE GOING
TO TRY TO FIND OUT
WHAT MOTHER NATURE'S
GOT WAITING FOR US.
Dustin: FRED WANTED
TO SHOW US YOUNG'UNS
HOW REAL WORK
IS DONE UNDERWATER.
Fred:
I'M LEAVING THEM OVER THERE
TO LET THEM GET
EVERYTHING READY FOR ME.
I'M HAVING CARLOS
CHECKING OUT A NEW MASK.
I'M GOING TO GO WITH A MORE
PROFESSIONAL-TYPE MASK.
I'VE ALREADY HAD TO DO
SOME COMMUNICATIONS CHANGES
TO MAKE IT WORK.
YEP. THAT SHOULD BE GOOD.
WE SHOULD BE GOOD TO GO.
AND WHEN THE WATER
IS NICE AND HOT
AND THE MASK IS
OPERATING PROPERLY...
THIS LOOKS GOOD.
...I'LL CRUISE OVER THERE
AND JUMP IN IT.
YEP. HERE HE COMES.
-HOLY [BLEEP] MAN.
-TODAY'S THE DAY, FELLAS.
HOW'D HE CHECK OUT
ON THAT MASK?
I THINK IT WORKED OUT GOOD,
FRED.
Narrator:
FRED'S STATE-OF-THE-ART MASK
HAS AN ADJUSTABLE
REGULATOR SYSTEM
TO MAKE BREATHING EASIER
IN THE FREEZING CONDITIONS.
HOPEFULLY THIS
MASK WORKS BETTER.
THAT SUCKS BEING DOWN THERE,
TRYING TO MOVE ALL THEM ROCKS,
STRUGGLING, AND YOU CAN'T
GET A FULL BREATH.
WEARS YOU OUT QUICK,
MAKES YOUR CHEEK MUSCLES HURT
FROM TRYING TO PULL
THAT AIR SO HARD.
Dustin:
FRED, HE WENT AND BOUGHT
THE MOST EXPENSIVE MASK
HE COULD FIND.
HOPEFULLY, TODAY,
HE COULD ACTUALLY USE IT
AND JUSTIFY A $3,500 MASK.
♪♪
Narrator:
FOR THE FIRST TIME,
FRED WILL BE ABLE
TO ACCESS THE AREA
WHERE DUSTIN FOUND HIS NUGGET.
OKAY. HOW IS THE HOT WATER
ON YOUR SUIT, FRED?
♪♪
I CAN SEE
THAT YOU'RE ABOUT 4 FEET OUT
FROM THE DIVE STATION,
ABOUT 2 FEET TO THE LEFT.
FRED: All right.
♪♪
[BLEEP]
IT'S GOT [BLEEP] COMMS, MAN.
IT'S -- MAN.
HAVING A HARD TIME
HEARING YOU, AS WELL.
[ STATIC ]
HEY, FRED!
Dustin: DID HE COPY?
THIS IS FRICKIN'
BULL[BLEEP] BROTHER.
THE COMMUNICATION'S
SO [BLEEP] UP.
Narrator:
CARLOS IS A COMMS EXPERT
AFTER A CAREER AS A MARINE
AND COMMERCIAL DIVER.
WE DIDN'T USE THE
COMMUNICATIONS FOR THAT MASK.
WE USED OUR OWN COMMUNICATIONS
AND JUST STUCK THEM IN THERE.
THAT'S DUCT TAPE
COMMUNICATIONS FOR RIGHT NOW.
FRED!
♪♪
ALL I CAN HEAR
IS THOSE DAMN BUBBLES.
HEY, FRED!
♪♪
HEY, FRED. THIS IS DUSTIN.
COPY, FRED?
FRED.
FRED, DO YOU COPY?
Dustin: FRED.
RESPOND OR SOMETHING.
Narrator:
FRED HURT IS DIVING FOR GOLD.
Dustin: ANY COMMS AT ALL.
Narrator: BUT HE'S LOST
ALL CONTACT WITH THE CREW.
♪♪
-BRING HIM UP!
-QUICK, BRING HIM UP!
-DIVER'S COMING OUT.
-WHAT HAPPENED?
[BLEEP] GET HIM OUT OF THERE.
GET HIM OUT OF THERE. HURRY.
HELP HIM OUT OF HERE.
GRAB HIM UNDER HIS ARM.
STAND HIM UP.
♪♪
-GOT HIM?
-YEAH.
[ GROANS ]
♪♪
-YOU OKAY, FRED?
-YEAH. I'M ALL RIGHT.
♪♪
Dustin: I'M SUITING UP.
GET HIM A HOT ROOM READY.
HELP HIM OUT
AND GET THE HOT ROOM READY.
Narrator:
DUSTIN SEIZES THE OPPORTUNITY
TO TAKE OVER FRED'S DIVE.
♪♪
WELL, I'VE GOT
THE HEATING ROOM GOING.
GO UP THERE AND GET
IN THAT HOT ROOM.
THAT'LL DEFINITELY
HELP YOU OUT, FRED.
I GOT IT GOING,
BEING WARMED UP.
♪♪
YEP. IT'LL BE GOOD
IN THE HOT ROOM, THOUGH.
GOT TO GET FRED TO SOME HEAT.
HE'S CHILLED.
HOLY [BLEEP]
THAT WAS A CLOSE CALL.
♪♪
Narrator: AT 38 DEGREES,
THESE GLACIAL WATERS
CAN KILL IN 15 MINUTES.
♪♪
THE FIRST SYMPTOMS
OF HYPOTHERMIA
ARE OFTEN FATIGUE AND CONFUSION.
I'M JUST SHAKING. MY WHOLE BODY
IS SHAKING RIGHT NOW.
-SOMETHING'S HAPPENED.
-GET YOU OVER THERE
AND GET YOU WARMED UP.
I'M GOING TO GET OVER
AND GET A LITTLE WARMED UP.
WELL, EVERY DIVE COUNTS
RIGHT NOW,
AND I NEED TO SEE GOLD.
FRED!
THAT WAS A CLOSE CALL.
Fred:
I DON'T HAVE ANY IDEA.
I DON'T HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW LONG I'VE BEEN DOWN.
NOT VERY LONG,
BUT IT DON'T TAKE LONG,
WHEN YOU'RE COLD,
TO GET HYPOTHERMIA,
ESPECIALLY IN WATER.
ONE THING IN AIR,
BUT, IN WATER,
IT'S PRETTY INSTANT.
AND YOU JUST CAN'T --
YOU JUST CAN'T -- AFTER A WHILE,
YOU JUST CAN'T STAND IT NO MORE.
YOUR BODY --
WHEN YOU'RE SHAKING INSIDE,
YOU KNOW IT AIN'T JUST 'CAUSE
YOU'RE [BLEEP] ABOUT BEING COLD.
IT IS COLD.
♪♪
Dustin:
YEAH. THAT'S WHAT I WOULD GUESS.
♪♪
WELL, I WEAR A LARGE.
-ALL RIGHT.
-I'M BIGGER THAN YOU.
WELL, WHATEVER.
♪♪
YOU GOT ALL YOUR CLOTHES
YOU NEED IN THERE, FRED?
Fred: OH, WET SOCKS.
♪♪
I FEEL A LOT BETTER.
LET'S GO!
Narrator:
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN SIX WEEKS,
DUSTIN CAN NOW DIVE DIRECTLY
ABOVE WHERE HE FOUND THE NUGGET.
♪♪
DUSTIN: Whoo-hoo!
[ Laughs ]
All right, well...
♪♪
Way to go, man! Whoo!
[ Laughing ]
Narrator: DUSTIN STARTS DREDGING
THE SURFACE OF THE CREEK BED.
THERE'S MORE THAN 10 FEET
OF BOULDERS AND RIVER GRAVEL
BETWEEN HIM AND THE GOLD DEPOSIT
HE BELIEVES LIES ON THE BEDROCK.
THAT'S ALL COMING THROUGH.
LOOK AT THAT.
♪♪
SO FAR, DUSTIN'S BEEN DREDGING
RIGHT AFTER FRED GOT OUT.
WE'RE GETTING A LOT OF STOP-UPS,
BUT THAT'S GOOD,
BECAUSE THAT MEANS A LOT
OF MATERIAL IS COMING THROUGH.
♪♪
-THERE IT IS.
-OH, IT'S IN THE --
IT'S IN THE NOZZLE!
Paul: HE SAID IT'S RIGHT THERE
IN YOUR NOZZLE.
♪♪
Whoo! This is great!
HE'S GETTING
A LOT OF REAL ESTATE
GOING RIGHT THROUGH
THIS SLUICE BOX,
SO THINGS ARE GOING GOOD.
WE NEVER KNOW, MAN.
WE MAY HAVE SOME NUGGETS
IN THERE RIGHT NOW.
♪♪
DIVER UP!
YEAH, IT'S NOT TOO BAD
THOUGH, MAN, YOU KNOW?
WE MOVED SOME DIRT TODAY.
-YEAH, WE DID.
-OH, MAN.
-BEAUCOUP DIRT, MAN.
-NOT A LOT OF ROCKS,
BUT A LOT OF DIRT.
I HOPE THERE'S GOLD
IN THIS STUFF, MAN.
Narrator: IN A 5-HOUR DIVE,
DUSTIN HAS DREDGED 2 FEET DOWN
AND PUMPED 15 YARDS OF GRAVEL
THROUGH THE SLUICE.
Carlos:
I DON'T WANT TO TOUCH IT, MAN.
I DON'T WANT TO PUT
MY HANDS IN THIS,
BUT THAT LOOKS LIKE SOMETHING.
I WANT TO GET PAUL OVER HERE
SO HE CAN LOOK AT THAT.
IT LOOKS LIKE A BIG
FRICKIN' NUGGET, MAN.
HEY, PAUL. COME LOOK AT THIS.
YOU KNOW GOLD MORE THAN I DO.
IS THAT A NUGGET OR WHAT?
♪♪
Paul: I SEE COLORS.
GOOD?
PAUL'S GOT A BIG SMILE
ON HIS FACE. MAYBE HE SAW GOLD.
-LOOKS GOOD.
-LOOKS BEAUTIFUL, DUDE.
PROBABLY PYRITE,
FOOL'S GOLD.
MOTHER [BLEEP] MAN!
COME ON. REALLY?
YEAH.
-REALLY?
-SEE HOW IT'S IN CUBE --
WHERE IT LOOKS LIKE
LITTLE CUBES?
[BLEEP] DUDE.
STOP AND THINK HOW MANY PEOPLE
IN THE OLD DAYS GOT TRICKED
BY THAT [BLEEP]
DIDN'T KNOW WHAT IT WAS.
YOU KNOW, YOU SEE
THE OLD-TIMERS BITE GOLD?
-YEAH.
-THAT'S WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
SEE ANYTHING
IN THERE, PAUL?
LOOK AT THAT.
WHAT'S THAT?
MORE PYRITE.
SEE HOW IT'S IN CUBES?
COME ON, PAUL!
HOPING TO SEE
SOME NUGGETS, MAN.
YEP.
Narrator: PYRITE IS A GOOD SIGN
YOU'RE CLOSE TO THE REAL THING,
BUT DUSTIN'S DIVE
HAS YIELDED ZERO GOLD.
I THINK THERE'S GOLD DOWN THERE.
I'M CONVINCED.
I KNOW IT'S THERE.
I JUST CAN'T GET TO IT.
WE ARE DEFINITELY
RUNNING OUT OF TIME,
AND WE DON'T NEED TO GO
ON A WILD GOOSE CHASE.
WE NEED TO GO FOR THE GOLD.
Narrator: UP AHEAD...
Carlos: I AM GOING INTO
THE MOUTH OF THE DRAGON
TODAY, BROTHER.
THAT'S WHERE THE GOLD'S AT, MAN.
[BLEEP]
CARLOS!
-HE'S DROWNING.
-GET HIM OUT OF THERE!
-GET HIM OUT OF THERE! HURRY!
-Coming out! Diver coming out!
♪♪
Fred: WE'VE ALL JUST GOT
A LITTLE BIT OF GOLD RIGHT NOW,
VERY LITTLE. PITIFUL, IN FACT.
WE JUST HAVEN'T
PRODUCED ANYTHING.
MAN, I'M WORE OUT.
ALL RIGHT.
Narrator:
TO FUND THEIR SEASON,
FRED TOOK A $50,000 LOAN
FROM TODD HOFFMAN.
BUT THREE MONTHS IN,
THE DAKOTA BOYS HAVE MINED
LESS THAN $1,000,
$49,000 SHORT
OF JUST BREAKING EVEN.
-WHAT, NO FIRE TONIGHT?
-NO, NOT YET.
YEAH.
COME CHECK IT OUT.
TODD PUT CARLOS ON THE TEAM
TO LOOK AFTER HIS INVESTMENT,
BUT HE'S BECOME A VALUED
MEMBER OF THE CREW.
I FEEL FOR FRED, YOU KNOW?
I FEEL FOR FRED BECAUSE HE KNOWS
HE HAS AN OBLIGATION
TO MR. HOFFMAN.
I GOT AN OBLIGATION
TO FRICKIN' TODD,
SO, YEAH.
I FEEL WHAT HE'S GOING
THROUGH RIGHT NOW.
Narrator: THREE WEEKS AGO,
TODD CAME TO CHECK ON THEM
AND GAVE THEM AN ULTIMATUM.
♪♪
Fred: TODD'S DEADLINE,
THAT'S COME AND GONE,
AND HE WANTS US TO MOVE
TO A DIFFERENT SITE
IF WE DON'T HAVE 20 OUNCES.
WE LOOKED AT SOME SITES,
AND...
TO ME, THEY LOOK LIKE
THE RIVER OF DEATH UP THERE
WHERE HE WAS
SUGGESTING GOING,
BUT HE DOESN'T KNOW
THIS CREEK,
NOT LIKE WE KNOW IT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WE'RE NOT MOVING.
WE'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
I MEAN, WE'RE BETTING THE FARM
ON THIS ONE, LITTLE SPOT.
WELL, THERE IS
NO POSSIBLE WAY FOR US
TO SET UP SHOP IN ANOTHER PLACE.
EASIER TO -- YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S NOT HAPPENING.
Man: THERE'S NO WAY.
IT'S NOT LIKE A BIG OPERATION
WHERE YOU'VE GOT MACHINES
TO MOVE ALL OF YOUR EQUIPMENT
AND THIS AND THAT.
EVERYTHING WE'RE DOING
IS BY HAND.
I DON'T CARE WHO SAYS WHAT.
-THIS IS MY CLAIM.
-THE PROBLEM IS
IS THAT TODD IS EXPECTING
TO GET PAID BACK $50,000.
DO YOU HAVE $50,000
TO GIVE HIM BACK?
♪♪
WE'RE GOING TO GET SOME GOLD.
IT'S GOING TO PAY OFF,
AND, IF IT DOESN'T,
THAT FALLS ON ME.
♪♪
WE'RE NOT MOVING.
I DON'T CARE WHO SAYS WHAT.
I'M THINKING,
IN THE BUSINESS SENSE, I --
I AM IN A TIGHT, TIGHT,
TIGHT SPOT HERE.
CARLOS, YOU JUST GOING
TO HAVE TO TELL TODD
THAT, "HEY,
THESE GUYS ARE ON IT."
I'LL DO SOMETHING ON MY END.
WE'RE STAYING WHERE WE'RE AT.
I DON'T CARE WHAT TODD HOFFMAN
OR ANYBODY ELSE SAYS.
HE CAN TRY TO TAKE
HIS EQUIPMENT BACK.
WE'LL SEE HOW THAT WORKS OUT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
♪♪
WHAT THE [BLEEP]
IS THAT, MAN?
[BLEEP]
Man:
CARLOS, WHAT'S GOING ON?
FRICKIN' CREEK
IS PRETTY MEAN TODAY.
♪♪
Narrator:
HEAVY RAINFALL OVERNIGHT
HAS RAISED THE CREEK LEVEL
BY 2 FEET.
[BLEEP] ALASKA, DUDE.
EVERYTHING HERE
IS TRYING TO KILL YOU, MAN.
♪♪
THE RAGING WATER IS SO HIGH,
THE DIVERSION IS NO LONGER
PROTECTING THE DIVE AREA.
Dustin: RIGHT NOW, ALL I'M
TRYING TO DO IS PATCH IT UP.
WE DON'T WANT ANYBODY TO DIE
IN HERE LOOKING FOR GOLD.
♪♪
Narrator:
EXPERT DIVER CARLOS MINOR
IS TAKING THE NEXT DIVE,
BUT HE'S USED TO THE CALM WATERS
OF THE GULF OF MEXICO.
THIS IS CARLOS' FIRST TIME
IN THE TURBULENT WATER.
I AM GOING INTO THE MOUTH
OF THE DRAGON TODAY, BROTHER.
THAT'S WHERE THE GOLD'S AT, MAN.
♪♪
Narrator: THE AREA
WHERE DUSTIN FOUND THE NUGGET
IS NOW A TORRENT
OF RAGING WHITEWATER.
CARLOS HAS TO STRUGGLE
AGAINST THE CURRENT
TO REMOVE A LAYER OF BOULDERS
AND GET DOWN TO WHERE THEY HOPE
TO FIND A MASSIVE
DEPOSIT OF GOLD.
♪♪
Dustin: GOING FOR THE LONG HAUL
RIGHT NOW, MAN.
I NEED YOU TO GO FARTHER
THAN WE'VE GONE.
ALL RIGHT.
Narrator:
TO COMBAT THE CURRENT,
CARLOS WILL BE WEARING
80 POUNDS OF LEAD,
THREE TIMES
HIS NORMAL DIVING WEIGHT.
Dustin: ONE OF THE WAYS WE KEEP
OUR GUYS ON THE BOTTOM
IS WEIGHING THEM DOWN.
WE JUST PUT MORE WEIGHT ON THEM.
-WHAT DO YOU THINK?
-I'LL GIVE IT A TRY, MAN.
♪♪
THIS IS THE HEAVIEST WEIGHT
EVER I WORE IN MY LIFE.
NOT THAT I CAN'T HANDLE IT,
BUT...
I NEVER HAD TO WEAR
SUCH HEAVY THINGS.
HERE WE GO, GOING INSIDE.
♪♪
Carlos:
HOLY [BLEEP] AAH.
FRED:
All right. Now is the time
to let Mother Nature
take its course.
YEP. OH, MY GOSH.
♪♪
Man: RIGHT NOW, THE WATER'S
SO TURBULENT UP THERE,
I CAN'T REALLY SEE WHERE
CARLOS' BUBBLES ARE COMING OUT.
BUT I THINK HE'S MAKING
HIS WAY UPSTREAM,
WHERE WE KNOW THAT
THOSE NUGGETS ARE AT.
♪♪
SOUNDED LIKE
HE WAS RIDING A HORSE
OR AN OLD BUCKING
BRONCO DOWN THERE.
♪♪
[ AIR HISSING,
CARLOS SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ]
♪♪
CARLOS!
[ CARLOS CONTINUES
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ]
HE'S DROWNING.
GET HIM OUT OF THERE!
-GET HIM OUT OF THERE! HURRY!
-Coming out! Diver coming out!
♪♪
GET HIM UP.
YEAH. I HEARD THAT,
AND I SAID, "UH-OH.
-SOMETHING'S HAPPENED."
-THAT WAS ROUGH.
THAT WAS PRETTY CRAZY,
WASN'T IT?
-WOW.
-WHOO!
WHAT HAPPENED, MAN,
YOUR MASK JUST OPENED UP?
SEAL BROKE OFF.
ONCE I STOOD UP, MAN,
ALL THAT FRICKIN' CURRENT
WENT RIGHT IN MY MASK, DUDE.
WHOO! DIDN'T YOU HEAR ME, MAN?
I WAS [BLEEP] DYING, DUDE.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
LET'S DO THIS, MAN.
-YOU SURE?
-YEAH. YEAH. YEAH.
-TAKE ANOTHER MINUTE OR TWO?
-I'M ON A MISSION, BRO.
I'M ON A MISSION.
THE LONGER I STAY OUT,
THE MORE NERVES GET [BLEEP]
FOR ME, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
LET'S GET HIM BACK DOWN
NOW, QUICK. GET HIM IN.
♪♪
MAN, HE'S DOING A GREAT JOB.
HE'S BRAVE.
HE'S PROVEN HE'S ONE OF US.
Narrator:
AFTER HIS CLOSE CALL,
CARLOS RETURNS
TO BATTLE THE BOULDERS.
♪♪
Dustin:
IT'S JUST A WEIRD-SHAPED ROCK.
RIGHT NOW, IT'S SITTING
ON THE EDGE OF THE HOLE,
AND IF THAT ROLLS IN THERE,
IT'LL KILL HIM.
SO WE GOT TO GET IT
OUT OF THE WAY.
CARLOS:
Oh. Easy. Easy. Easy. Easy.
Be careful, guys.
Don't -- Don't -- Don't jerk it.
♪♪
Dustin: THAT'S WHERE
SHE'S SITTING FOR NOW.
Whoo-hoo!
♪♪
CARLOS:
Keep going. It's moving.
Narrator:
CARLOS MINOR IS ATTEMPTING TO
GET THROUGH A LAYER OF BOULDERS,
DOWN TO A GOLD DEPOSIT
ON THE BEDROCK
WORTH MILLIONS OF DOLLARS.
CARLOS: It's in the claw,
but I just got to make sure
it stays in the claw.
RIGHT NOW, WE'RE GETTING
INTO A GIANT WALL
OF THAT-SIZE ROCKS.
TYPICALLY, GOLD HANGS OUT
WHERE THE BIGGER ROCKS HANG OUT,
AND THE BIGGER THE ROCKS,
IN OUR HEAD, THE BETTER.
♪♪
IT'S A STRUGGLE, 'CAUSE WE DON'T
HAVE THE RIGHT EQUIPMENT
TO GET THESE DAMN ROCKS OUT.
♪♪
CARLOS: Holy moly!
Whoo-hoo!
HE JUST MOVED A TREMENDOUS
AMOUNT OF ROCKS TODAY,
WHICH IS HELPING
US OUT IMMENSELY.
-IMPRESSED, MAN!
-LET'S DO IT.
Narrator: AFTER CLEARING
A LAYER OF BOULDERS,
CARLOS CAN FINALLY
START DREDGING FOR GOLD.
CARLOS: All right, Paul.
You're the man, brother.
CRANK IT UP!
♪♪
Sweet.
Frickin' nailed it, brother.
♪♪
FRED:
Yeah. You're about 3 or 4 feet
in front of the walkway here,
and you're about 8 feet out.
-Doing great.
-Good position, right?
-I'm still in the same spot.
-Yes, it is. Yes, it is.
Okay.
♪♪
Yes.
DIVER UP!
YES, SIR.
GREAT DIVE. GOOD DIVE.
GOOD JOB, MAN!
ALL FRICKIN' ROCKS STOP
ON TOP OF EACH OTHER.
BIG, BIG, SO THEY'RE
ABOUT THAT BIG, RIGHT?
YEAH, LIKE THAT BIG.
LIKE THESE [BLEEP]
Paul:
THERE IS GOLD IN HERE.
-IS THERE?
-YEAH.
YOU GOT GOLD,
BY THE WAY.
WHAT?!
IT'S NOT A BIG PIECE,
BUT --
[BLEEP] THAT'S GOLD!
I DON'T GIVE A [BLEEP] MAN.
THAT'S [BLEEP] GOLD!
THAT'S IT, MAN! THAT'S IT. I
DON'T GIVE A [BLEEP] WHAT IT IS.
-IT'S GOLD, BRO.
-THERE IS GOLD.
THAT'S GOLD! [BLEEP] YEAH,
IT'S GOLD! DAMN RIGHT IT'S GOLD!
I MADE THAT [BLEEP] GOLD.
HE'S GOT THE FEVER!
-WHOO-HOO!
-WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
IT'S THERE, MAN!
IT'S RIGHT THERE!
THAT'S WHERE I FOUND
THAT [BLEEP]
Dustin: IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN ME,
BUT YOU FOUND IT.
[BLEEP] YEAH,
I FOUND THAT GOLD.
-CAN YOU SEE IT?
-YEAH. YOU CAN SEE IT.
[BLEEP] YEAH,
THAT'S GOLD!
Paul: CARLOS IS DEFINITELY
MOVING UPSTREAM
AND GETTING IN
THE RIGHT SPOT.
GOT US A LITTLE PICKER
RIGHT THERE,
BUT THERE'S NO TELLING WHAT'S UP
UNDERNEATH THESE RIPPLES STILL.
THERE'S STILL A LOT
OF GOOD AREA UP THERE
THAT COULD HAVE
A LOT MORE SMALL GOLD.
Narrator:
IT'S ONLY A SMALL PICKER,
BUT IT'S COME FROM RIGHT ABOVE
WHERE DUSTIN THINKS
THEY'LL FIND A HUGE DEPOSIT.
♪♪
Dustin:
JUST AS I PREDICTED,
THE GOLD IS EXACTLY WHERE
I SAID IT WAS GOING TO BE.
TODAY, CARLOS JUMPED IN
AND NAILED IT.
THERE'S GOLD IN THERE,
AND HE FOUND IT.
BIG-TIME HAPPY, BRO.
TELL MR. HOFFMAN,
"I FOUND YOUR GOLD, MAN,
SO LEAVE THESE GUYS ALONE,"
YOU KNOW? [BLEEP]
"LEAVE THEM ALONE, MAN.
JUST LET US DO OUR THING."
SO THAT'S A GOOD SIGN. THAT'S
A GOOD FRICKIN' SIGN, MAN.
HE'LL PUT US BACK
ON THE BOARD, BRO, YOU KNOW?
PUT US BACK ON
THE BOARD, FRICKIN' --
SEE WHAT I'M DOING RIGHT?
THAT'S [BLEEP] YEAH, BRO.
YOU DO IT. YEAH.
YOU SAY IT. YEAH.
-YOU SAY IT. YEAH.
-YEAH!
[BLEEP] YEAH, MAN. YEAH, BRO.
♪♪
HERE'S YOUR FIRST
PIECE OF VISIBLE GOLD
SITTING IN THE BACK
OF THE SLUICE AREA.
IT'S NOT VERY BIG,
-BUT THERE IT IS, DUDE.
-HEY.
Dustin: THERE'S PLENTY OF GOLD
BACK THERE.
THAT'S JUST WHAT
HE COULD SEE AND PICK OUT.
YEAH. THAT'S JUST THE ONE
OBVIOUS PIECE SO WE KNOW
-THAT THERE'S PLENTY --
-YOU PICK THAT OUT, MAN?
-YOU CAN SEE THAT [BLEEP]
-YEAH.
SO EVERY TIME WE GET CLOSER
TO THAT SPOT, THERE'S GOLD.
YEAH. THERE'S GOLD, BRO.
HELLO, BABY.
THAT'S IT.
IT'S RIGHT THERE.
ALL WE GOT TO DO
IS GO DIG IT OUT NOW.
ONCE WE GET DOWN
TO THE BOTTOM RIGHT THERE,
WHEN WE HIT THE BEDROCK
RIGHT THERE, DUDE,
IT'S GOING TO BE
SO MUCH GOLD
WE'RE NOT GOING
TO KNOW WHAT TO DO.
[BLEEP] DANG RIGHT, RIGHT?
[BLEEP] [BLEEP] YEAH.
-I'M A GOLD MINER, BRO.
-YOU WERE JUST A ROCK MOVER.
NOW YOU'RE A GOLD DREDGER.
♪♪
Narrator:
ON THE NEXT EPISODE...
♪♪
I THINK WE'RE
GOING TO FIND GOLD.
WE'RE REALLY DAMN CLOSE,
REALLY CLOSE.
FRED: Maybe that's where the
gold is, right underneath it.
YEAH!
[BLEEP] [BLEEP]
GOT POWER IN THE WATER!
I GOT HIT.
-HOLY [BLEEP]
-THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S A BEAUTIFUL PIECE
OF GOLD RIGHT THERE.
THIS IS WHAT WE'VE BEEN
LOOKING FOR, MAN, RIGHT?
-YEP, THAT'S IT.
-THAT'S IT RIGHT THERE, MAN.