**
IT'S LIKE GETTING HOOKED
ON CRACK OR SOMETHING, HUH?
Paul: COPY THAT.
Dustin: COME ON [BLEEP]
[ GROANS ]
**
Fred: I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THIS.
Dustin: PLEASE,
DON'T LET HIM DIE.
FREAKING MAD MAN.
WOO-HOO!
THIS IS CRAZY!
-WE GOT BEARS OVER HERE, BRO.
-I DON'T GOT MY GUN ON ME.
IT'S IN MY BACKPACK.
-WHAT?!
Wes: LOOK AT THAT PIECE
OF GOLD RIGHT THERE.
WOO-HOO!
Dustin: WE FOUND NUGGETS.
-CLEAN THAT SUCKER OUT!
-WOO!
OUR TIME HAS COME.
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
DISCOVERY COMMUNICATIONS
**
WE FOUND SOME GOLD LAST WEEK,
JUST A SIGN WAS ALL WE NEEDED.
TODAY, WE'RE GONNA
CHARGE FULL STEAM AHEAD.
EVERYBODY'S EXCITED,
MORALE'S HIGH.
THERE'S A HUGE DEPOSIT
IN THAT PLUNGE POOL.
I CAN FEEL IT.
Narrator: ONE MONTH IN,
THE DAKOTA BOYS
ARE ALREADY ON THE GOLD.
-YOU GUYS READY?
-YEP.
Narrator: NOW THEY'RE HEADING
OUT TO DREDGE McKINLEY CREEK
FOR THE SECOND TIME THIS SEASON.
Dustin: I KNOW THERE'S GOLD
DOWN THERE.
IT'S JUST SO DAMN HARD
TO GET TO.
Fred: LET'S GET OUT THERE.
LET'S GET SOME GOLD.
Narrator: THE MINE SITE
IS SO REMOTE...
Wes: WOO! SEE, THAT'S
YOUR HYPER-SPEED RIGHT THERE.
...THE DAKOTA BOYS
MUST RISK THEIR LIVES
EVERY TIME THEY HEAD OUT.
READY? HERE WE GO.
WOO-HOO!
THIS IS CRAZY!
COMMERCIAL DIVER CARLOS MINOR
HAS BEEN AT McKINLEY
FOR JUST A FEW DAYS.
Minor: YEP, WORRIED
ABOUT THE BEARS OVER HERE, BRO.
I MEAN, NOT GETTING MUGGED
OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
I MEAN, BEARS ARE, LIKE, ENOUGH,
FREAKIN' EAT YOU.
HERE'S THESE BEAR TRACKS
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT.
BEAR TRACKS?
[BLEEP] I DON'T GOT
MY GUN ON ME.
-IT'S IN MY BACKPACK.
-WHAT?
I AM NOT FREAKIN'
DYING OUT HERE, BRO.
Narrator: MINERS HAVE DIED
IN THIS REMOTE ALASKAN CANYON.
IT'S THAT DANGER THAT'S KEPT
THEM FROM GETTING TO THE GOLD
UP McKINLEY CREEK
AND THE REMOTE BEND
WITH A PLUNGE POOL
THAT THE DAKOTA BOYS BELIEVE
WILL MAKE THEM RICH.
THE RUSHING WATER DROPS
INTO THE PLUNGE POOL, SLOWS.
AND GOLD DROPS OUT.
THE GOLD THEY FOUND LAST WEEK
ON THE SURFACE
INDICATES THAT,
DOWN ON THE BEDROCK,
THERE COULD BE
A DEPOSIT BIG ENOUGH
TO COVER THEIR $50,000 COSTS
AND LET THEM LEAVE MILLIONAIRES.
THIS IS SOME UGLY WATER TODAY,
AND IT'S HIGH.
THIS IS DANGEROUS. AAH.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO TALK
ABOUT THIS WITH THE GUYS.
Wes: IT'S JUST A TORRENT
OF MUDDY MESS.
NO TELLING WHAT KIND OF LOGS ARE
GONNA BE COMING DOWN ANY TIME.
I WOULDN'T BLAME HIM
IF HE DIDN'T WANT TO DIVE TODAY.
I WOULDN'T.
Narrator:
TO GET TO THE TREASURE,
DUSTIN MUST DIVE
IN A SURGING TORRENT,
POWERFUL ENOUGH TO ROLL
HALF-TON BOULDERS
ALONG THE CREEK BED.
I'M RATTLED RIGHT NOW.
IT'S CRAZY.
IT MAY NOT LOOK LIKE
MUCH FROM UP HERE.
BUT, MAN, IS IT BAD UNDER THERE.
IT'LL RIP YOUR DAMN CLOTHES
RIGHT OFF YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, YOU GOT TO LISTEN TO ME
AND BEING REAL RIGHT NOW.
I'M NOT JUST JUMPING
IN THE WATER.
THAT'S NOT HOW THIS
IS GONNA WORK
'CAUSE I'M NOT
FEELING A LITTLE --
I'M NOT FEELING
VERY GREAT ABOUT THIS.
MAN, THIS WATER'S
CRAZY TODAY.
HEY,
JUST IF ANYTHING HAPPENS --
LET'S JUST AGREE
ON SOMETHING.
IF SOMETHING'S WRONG,
JUST SAY, "DIVER UP!"
AND THEN, EVERYBODY'S ONBOARD
JUST TO BRING HIM UP
NO MATTER WHAT.
NO, "WHY?" NO, THIS...
-YEAH, GOOD.
-YEAH, SOUNDS GREAT.
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
THAT'S WONDERFUL.
YOU'RE BRINGING IT.
THAT'S A WONDERFUL THING
TO BRING TO THE TABLE, ACTUALLY.
THANK YOU.
I NEED YOU
TO PUT ME ON BELAY.
YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO DRAG ME OUT OF THE WATER
IF THERE'S A PROBLEM.
Dustin:
FRED, ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M STILL JUDGING THINGS
OUT THERE...
WELL, THEN STOP IT.
JUST STOP IT.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE
IN CHARGE.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO CHANGE ANYTHING.
JUST LET'S DO THIS,
MAN.
THE DEAD LOG IS
TOO HIGH OUT OF THE WATER.
LEAVE IT ALONE.
NO.
IT'S TOO HIGH
OUT OF THE WATER.
LET'S NOT START MODIFYING
[BLEEP] RIGHT NOW
WHEN I'M ABOUT TO GO
IN THE DAMN WATER.
I DON'T LIKE IT.
I'M TRYING TO PREVENT
A PROBLEM BEFORE IT HAPPENS.
IF IT'S A PROBLEM,
WE'LL FIX IT, FRED.
IF NOT, THEN WHO CARES?
IT'S ONE LITTLE BOLT.
WE TAKE IT OUT.
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
I JUST FIGURED WE OUGHTA DO IT
RIGHT NOW, AND NOT LATER,
THAT'S ALL.
WOULD YOU JUST...
DAMN IT!
I JUST WANT TO [BLEEP]
DO THIS RIGHT!
FRED, I LOVE YOU, MAN. COME ON!
WHY YOU GOT TO HAVE A PROBLEM?
JUST LET IT HAPPEN.
THIS IS OKAY.
I'M FRUSTRATED RIGHT NOW.
I DON'T WANT TO BE.
COME ON. LET'S JUST DO IT.
IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE
A PROBLEM.
WE'RE OKAY.
LET'S JUST DO IT.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY GOOD?
-YEP.
-ALL RIGHT.
SAME OLD BULL [BLEEP]
WON'T [BLEEP] DAMN LISTEN.
FRED JUST DOESN'T WANT TO GIVE
UP RESPONSIBILITY TO DUSTIN.
HE THINKS HE CONTINUALLY NEEDS
TO TELL HIM WHAT TO DO.
Minor: THAT'S A DANG ALPHA DEAL,
YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, FATHER, SON --
SON, FATHER.
I'M JUST SORRY THAT, YOU KNOW,
THAT THINGS GOT
A LITTLE RILED UP.
BUT IT'S NOT A GOOD WAY
TO GO DIVING,
WHEN YOU'RE ALL RILED UP
AND FRUSTRATED.
YOU NEED TO BE REALLY,
REALLY FROSTY ABOUT DIVING.
-LET'S GO.
-WE'RE READY TO DREDGE.
ALL WE NEED IS A DIVER.
YOU READY, DUSTIN?
HERE WE GO.
YOU GOT AIR?
DEEP BREATHS, MAN,
DEEP BREATHS.
HOW'S YOUR HOT WATER?
STILL DOING GOOD?
Narrator: DUSTIN IS DREDGING
RIGHT WHERE FRED
FOUND GOLD LAST WEEK.
DUSTIN IS USING THAT DREDGE,
WORKING IT AROUND,
AND IT'S JUST A, LIKE,
A GIANT VACUUM CLEANER.
AND HE'S DREDGING A HOLE,
AND WE'RE JUST TRYING
TO GET DOWN AS DEEP AS WE CAN.
Narrator: THE HOSE SUCKS GRAVEL
FROM THE CREEK BED,
UP INTO THE DREDGE
AND THROUGH THE SLUICE BOX
WHERE THE RIPPLES
CATCH THE GOLD.
Fred: I LOVE IT, MAN!
I MEAN, IT WAS WORKING!
Wes: YEP! EVERYTHING IS
WORKING PERFECT.
YOU NOTICE
THERE'S NO MUD IN THAT?
NO, THAT'S CLEAN
RIGHT THERE.
FLUSHED ROCK.
YEAH.
THAT'S NOT DEPOSIT.
THAT'S GLACIER ROCK.
THAT'S GOOD.
IF WE CAN KEEP THIS UP
FOR A COUPLE HOURS...
I THINK IF WE GET DOWN TO
THE VERY BOTTOM OF THIS THING,
I THINK, WE'RE GONNA DO
VERY, VERY WELL.
**
WELL, I'M TELLING YOU
HOWS, MAN,
WOUND UP GETTING
THE GOLD FEVER, HUH?
[BLEEP] DAMN.
IT'S LIKE GETTING HOOKED
ON CRACK OR SOMETHING, HUH?
AH, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
JUST GET THE JOB DONE.
-THAT'S ALL WE LOOKING FOR.
-YEAH.
THAT'S ALL WE'RE LOOKING FOR
RIGHT NOW
IS LET'S GET THE JOB DONE.
WE'RE DOING GREAT.
FIND THAT GOLD, MAN.
FIND THAT GOLD.
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE'RE
FINALLY DOING THIS, MAN.
Dustin: WOO-HOO!
YEAH!
**
COPY THAT.
THAT'S WHERE
THE GOLD LIES, THOUGH.
Narrator: A DEPOSIT BIG ENOUGH
TO MAKE THEM RICH
WILL MOST LIKELY BE
IN THE TURBULENT WATER
AROUND THE PLUNGE POOL.
OKAY.
I GOT YOUR BACK.
Dustin: COME ON [BLEEP]
[ GROANS ]
DUSTIN!!
Narrator: DUSTIN HURT
IS DIVING FOR GOLD
IN THE RAGING RAPIDS
OF McKINLEY CREEK.
Dustin: COME ON [BLEEP]
[ GROANS ]
DUSTIN!!
**
WHAT HAPPENED?
[ GROANING ]
DIVER'S COMING IN!
OH [BLEEP]
NO, THAT WOULDN'T BE GOOD.
THAT WAS SCARY
AS HELL, MAN.
-OH, I BET.
-CRAZY SCARY.
LET'S NOT DO THAT AGAIN.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT ROCKS
HITTING US IN THE HEAD NOW.
IT'S A BIG PROBLEM.
Paul: I DON'T WANT TO GET HIT
IN THE HEAD EITHER.
NO. HELL NO.
GET OUT OF THAT
METEOR SHOWER, MAN.
THAT REALLY,
REALLY BEAT ME UP.
ALL RIGHT. I JUST NEED
TO SIT DOWN FOR NOW.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
JUST RELAX, JUST RELAX.
I'M JUST GONNA SIT DOWN
IN THAT CHAIR AND...
Narrator: DUSTING'S
DEATH-DEFYING 2-HOUR DIVE
HAS PUT AROUND 3 CUBIC YARDS
OF RIVER GRAVEL
THROUGH THEIR SLUICE.
Wes: FRED,
LOOK AT THAT, RIGHT THERE
I SEE IT.
HOLY [BLEEP] WOO!
THAT IS WHAT IT LOOKS
LIKE, ISN'T IT?
Paul: I THINK
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT IT IS.
THERE'S A LITTLE NUGGET
IN THERE.
IT'S SITTING THERE,
RIGHT NEXT TO A SCREW,
OF ALL THINGS,
THAT WE DROPPED
IN THE DAMN THING.
-GET OVER HERE!
-COME ON!
MAYBE IT'LL
WARM YOU UP, MAN!
OH, HE'S GONNA BE HAPPY!
-WOO-HOO!
-DAMN!
YEAH!
-WOO! WOO!
-WOO!
LISTEN TO YOU.
YOU GET TO PICK IT
OUT OF THE BOX.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
NUGGETS.
-COME ON!
-I CAN'T COME DOWN THERE.
-THE HELL YOU CAN'T...
GET YOUR ASS DOWN HERE!
RIGHT NEXT TO THAT SCREW,
BUDDY.
WELL, I'LL BE DAMNED.
WE FOUND...
WE FOUND NUGGETS.
-YEAH!
-WOO-HOO!
WE FOUND NUGGETS.
[ CHUCKLING ]
THAT'S BIGGER
THAN WE'VE EVER GOT
FROM PORCUPINE CREEK!
THAT'S RIGHT!
-WOO!
-CLEAN THAT SUCKER OUT!
Wes: WAY TO GO, BUDDY!
Paul: GOOD JOB, MAN.
OUR TIME HAS COME.
WE GOT SOME GOLD.
IT'S ONLY GONNA GET BIGGER.
Paul: IT'S ONLY GONNA
GET BIGGER, MAN.
I'M GONNA GO PUT
SOME DAMN CLOTHES ON!
-NICE PIECE OF GOLD.
-YEAH!
A BIG SON OF A [BLEEP]
-WE ARE GONNA BE RICH, MAN!
-YEAH!
WELL, I'M --
I'M SPEECHLESS.
EVERYTHING WE WAS BRAGGING ABOUT
AND TALKING ABOUT,
HEY, IT'S COMING THROUGH.
WE DIDN'T EXPECT TO FIND
A NUGGET THAT BIG THIS QUICK.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT WE FOUND GOLD.
I HOPE THIS MAKES ME
A RICH MAN.
I WANT TO BE RICH.
I WANT TO HAVE GOLD
STACKED UP TO THE CEILING.
Fred: THIS WILL BE
A MEMORABLE MOMENT FOR ME,
FIRST BIG NUGGET OUT
OF McKINLEY CREEK HERE.
I THINK THERE'S GONNA BE
A LOT MORE TO FOLLOW.
Dustin: I'M JUST GETTING
STARTED, JUST GETTING STARTED.
THAT WAS LIKE
A TEST DIVE FOR ME.
DAMN, THIS FEELS GOOD.
I JUST -- I'M IN DISBELIEF,
THOUGH, RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS INCREDIBLE.
**
I DON'T LIKE
WHAT'S HAPPENING ANYMORE.
Narrator: FINDING A BIG NUGGET
PROVES THE DAKOTA BOYS
ARE ON THE GOLD.
BUT DIVING UNPROTECTED
COULD KILL THEM.
I BEEN NONSTOP THINKING
ABOUT WHAT WE'RE DOING
OUT THERE RIGHT NOW.
IT'S DANGEROUS,
AND I THINK IT'S IMPORTANT
TO NOT GET OUR BRAINS
SMASHED IN OUT HERE.
YEAH, 'CAUSE I WAS
LOOKING AT THAT MYSELF.
AND I SAID, "MAN,
WE GOT TO DO SOMETHING."
'CAUSE WE'RE NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO BREAK THROUGH THAT CURRENT
WITHOUT GETTING THE WRATH
OF THAT CREEK
POURED DOWN ON TOP OF US.
WHAT ABOUT THIS?
YOU REMEMBER THE DIVERSION
I-BEAM WE MADE
FOR COUPLE YEARS AGO,
THAT WE WERE GONNA USE
AT THE WATERFALL?
-YEAH.
IT'S STILL AT PORCUPINE.
WE NEVER USED IT.
WHY DON'T WE PUT THAT IN
RIGHT UP THERE BY THE BRIDGE?
WE CAN SHOOT THAT WATER
OFF THAT WAY.
AND THEN WE CAN WORK
THAT WHOLE TOP OFF.
AND WE CREATE A CALM AREA THERE
WHERE WE FOUND THAT NUGGET AT.
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA, MAN.
IT'S JUST --
HOW ARE YOU
GONNA CARRY IT OUT THERE?
SOME OF IT'S JUST
NOT EVEN JUST HEAVY.
IT'S JUST
AWKWARD AS HELL TO CARRY.
WE'RE GONNA NEED
A HELICOPTER LIFT --
A ONE 30-MINUTE RIDE.
OKAY, THAT'S WHAT
WE SHOULD WORK ON TODAY
BECAUSE I'M WORRIED,
IF WE GO OUT THERE
AND DIG FOR ONE MORE DAY,
THIS IS GONNA GET
SO DANGEROUS
THAT THOSE ROCKS ARE GONNA
START ROLLING IN ON YOU.
I TELL YOU WHAT.
IT'LL STAND OVER HERE
AGAINST THIS SIDE, OKAY?
Narrator: THE 16-FOOT-LONG
STEEL CONSTRUCTION BEAM
HAS ALREADY BEEN CUSTOMIZED
BY WES
TO SUPPORT 8x2 TIMBER PLANKS.
WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO IS TAKE
BOARDS OF VARYING LENGTHS.
WE'RE GONNA SLIDE THEM
INTO THIS DIVERSION
AND JUST PUSH THEM
STRAIGHT DOWN IN
UNTIL THEY DROP DOWN
AND HIT ON TOP OF THE ROCK.
AND WE'LL DO THAT
ON EVERY ONE.
WE'LL JUST KEEP GOING UNTIL
WE'VE GOT A REALLY GOOD LITTLE,
WHAT THEY CALL
A PEN LEVY.
THE PLAN --
FIX THE BEAM TO THE CREEK WALL,
ANCHORING IT
WITH A POLE AND CABLE.
THEN, ATTACH THE LINE OF PLANKS
RIGHT DOWN TO THE CREEK BED.
THE DIVERSION SHOULD
DEFLECT ANY BOULDERS
AND CREATE A CALM AREA
WHERE THEY CAN DREDGE FOR GOLD.
YOU CAN'T WORK
IN THAT WATERFALL.
THAT CURRENT IS
JUST TOO VICIOUS.
Narrator: FRED PREPARES
THE DIVERSION LOAD
FOR A HELI-LIFT UP TO THE CREEK.
Fred: THIS, RIGHT HERE,
IS GONNA ELIMINATE 90%
OF ALL THAT CURRENT.
HEY, THIS IS GONNA HELP US
GET THAT GOLD.
THIS 2-MILE TRANSPORT WILL
COST FRED CLOSE TO $1,500
OUT OF THE $50,000 HE BORROWED
FROM TODD HOFFMAN
AT THE BEGINNING OF THE SEASON.
Fred: WE'RE NOT SPENDING IT
ON ANY FRIVOLOUS-TYPE THINGS,
STRICTLY FOR THINGS
THAT WE THINK
ARE GONNA HELP US GET GOLD.
Narrator: BEFORE ANY OF THE CREW
MAKES A CENT THIS YEAR,
THEY FIRST NEED TO FIND
42 OUNCES OF GOLD
TO PAY BACK TODD'S LOAN.
GOOD LIFT, MAN!
A GOOD LIFT!
Dustin: SO WE'RE
GONNA PUT THIS THING IN HERE
SO WE CAN REDIRECT THIS WATER
OVER TO THE LEFT OVER HERE.
Wes: WELL, I WAS THINKING,
YOU WANT TO HANG IT ON, LIKE...
Paul: I THINK
RIGHT OFF THIS POINT.
-THAT'S WHAT I KEEP LOOKING AT.
-SOMETHING RIGHT THERE.
YEAH, IT LOOKS
LIKE A GOOD POINT.
WE COULD PUT THAT LEG
IN IT THERE
AND THEN,
PULL IT AROUND.
AS SOON AS WE PUT
THIS DIVERSION IN,
WE CAN DIG ALL THAT OUT.
LOOK HOW ANGRY
THIS THING IS, MAN.
THEY WANT TO DEFLECT THIS WATER.
WOW, MAN.
HERE SHE COMES!
Minor: HOLY [BLEEP] MAN.
Paul: JUST GET BACK.
JUST STAY BACK!
-SO THIS IS OUR DIVERSION?
-YEP.
Narrator:
THE MODIFIED CONSTRUCTION BEAM
WEIGHS 430 POUNDS.
COMING DOWN.
-WOO!
-YEAH!
WORKING BEAST, MAN.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE GONNA COME TO ME
AND THEN GO OUT A LITTLE BIT.
A LITTLE BIT MORE.
HOLD ON. HOLD ON.
YOU'RE LOSING OR WHAT?
-CAN YOU KEEP IT ON THAT DECK?
-YEAH.
RIGHT THERE.
ALL RIGHT.
-GOT IT, WES?
-YEAH. OH!
Wes: [BLEEP] WHAT JUST
HAPPENED THERE?
Dustin: [BLEEP] DAMN.
I GOT IT.
NO, IT'S GOOD.
AH! THAT HURT.
I'M IMPRESSED
WITH ALL THESE GUYS.
WHEN THEY PUT THEIR
HEADS TOGETHER,
THEY COME UP WITH
SOME INTERESTING STUFF.
LOOKING GOOD SO FAR.
I GOT TO GET SOME WADERS ON,
GET OVER THERE
AND HELP THEM OUT.
Narrator:
FOR THE DIVERSION TO WORK,
IT MUST BE FIRMLY FIXED
TO THE CREEK WALL.
THAT'S GOOD!
THAT'S GOOD RIGHT THERE.
Dustin: CARLOS!
PLEASE DON'T LET HIM DIE.
OH, I GOT YOU.
BETTER MAKE SURE!
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THIS.
**
Dustin: GOT TO JAM IT IN
REAL HARD.
THAT'S OLD-SCHOOL [BLEEP]
RIGHT THERE.
THAT'S WHAT WE LIKE
TO CALL DANGEROUS.
WE'RE TRYING TO GET US
A HOLE DRILLED
INTO THE BACK END
OF THIS BEAM HERE
SO WE CAN SLIDE A BOLT IN
SO IT HOLDS IT UP.
THE ONLY THING HOLDING IT
IS THIS ROPE RIGHT NOW.
Narrator: EX-CONSTRUCTION BOSS
FRED HURT IS IN HIS ELEMENT.
HE'S FIXING
THE STEEL DIVERSION BEAM
TO THE SHALE ROCK TO CREATE
A SAFE ZONE TO DIVE IN.
WOO.
IT'S GONNA
TAKE A WHILE, FOLKS.
SURE YOU DON'T WANT ME
TO DO THIS FOR YOU?
I GOT IT.
GOT ABOUT A FEW
MORE INCHES TO GO.
FRED'S TAKEN OVER
MY PLAN.
IT AIN'T GOING
NOWHERE NOW!
WOO!
Minor: YOU SEE WHAT FRED
DID RIGHT DOWN THERE?
FREAKING A MAD MAN.
WHOA! HOLY [BLEEP]
WE'RE READY
TO PUT BOARDS IN THERE
IN JUST, LIKE,
UGH, JUST A FEW MINUTES.
HEY, FRED,
THAT'S NOT STABLE, BY THE WAY.
I-I KNOW
IT'S NOT STABLE.
OKAY, AS LONG AS YOU KNOW
DON'T FALL IN.
OH [BLEEP]
SEE IF THIS WORKS.
THAT'S PERFECT.
FRED'S 72.
AND HE LOVES TO BE
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE WORK.
NOT HOLDING BACK.
Wes: THERE IS ONE
THAT'S SHORTER.
Minor: FREAKIN' AMAZING, RIGHT?
LOOK AT THIS.
HOLY CRAP.
Fred: IT'S ALREADY STOPPED
THE CURRENT OVER HERE.
WE GOT IT!
GOOD JOB, GUYS!
Paul: DUSTIN,
THIS ISN'T WORKING.
THAT IS A LOT OF WATER.
Dustin: YEAH, THERE'S
DEFINITELY TOO MUCH WATER
COMING THROUGH TO THE DIVERSION.
I DIDN'T THINK THERE'D BE
EVEN HALF THIS WATER.
Narrator: McKINLEY CREEK FLOWS
AT 8 TONS PER SECOND.
THE HALF-INCH GAPS ARE LETTING
TOO MUCH WATER THROUGH.
WE DIDN'T TALK ABOUT
THIS WHOLE THING.
HOW YOU GONNA DO THIS?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT ELSE
TO DO RIGHT NOW.
DO YOU HAVE A --
A SOLUTION?
WHY DON'T WE JUST TAKE
A PIECE OF PLYWOOD
AND SHOVE IT ALL THE WAY
TO THE LEFT?
WELL, PLYWOOD IS GONNA BEND.
I MEAN, IT'S --
NO, IT'LL BE RIGHT UP
AGAINST THE WALL.
OKAY.
SO WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO GET
SOME PLYWOOD AND PUT IT IN --
JAM IT DOWN THERE SIDEWAYS,
PIN IT TO THE WALL.
HE CAN'T HELP
BUT STAND OVER MY SHOULDER
AND TELL ME WHAT TO DO.
Fred: LET'S SEE IF WE CAN
MAKE THIS THING WORK.
UGH!
**
FRED ALWAYS THINKS
HE KNOWS BEST.
AND HE'S -- HE'S GOT
A LOT OF AGE ON ME.
BUT THAT'S NOT THE SAME THING.
YOU CAN'T REALLY EXPLAIN
THAT TO A FRED HURT, THOUGH.
[ CHUCKLING ]
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO OVER WITH IT A LITTLE.
Minor: WHERE ARE WE GOING?
IT'S GONNA GO STRAIGHT
DOWN RIGHT THERE.
-OVER THE EDGE?
-YEAH.
OKAY.
HERE WE GO.
THIS IS GONNA BE CRAZY.
YOU GOT A HOLD
OF IT?
YEP, GOT A HOLD OF IT.
COME ON!
WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU ADD FRED HURT,
A FULL SHEET OF PLYWOOD,
AND RAGING WATER?
THIS CAN'T BE ANYTHING
BUT CHAOS.
IT WOULD BE NICE TO HAVE
SOME HELP DOWN THERE.
BUT I GUESS EVERYBODY
IS GONNA STAND THERE AND WATCH.
HELLS YEAH!
ALL RIGHT?
I'LL SEE IF I CAN WRESTLE
THE DAMN THING INTO PLACE.
ALL RIGHT.
RESCUE TIME.
Paul: NOT MUCH
TO HOLD ON TO HERE.
HOLD ON A SECOND. I'LL GIVE YOU
A HAND IN A SECOND.
I-I GOT TO GET MYSELF
IN POSITION.
COMING DOWN WITH IT!
A FULL SHEET OF PLYWOOD.
AND HE MADE THAT [BLEEP] WORK.
NOW WE'RE GETTING
SOMEWHERE.
HERE YOU GO.
YEAH! GOT IT!
Dustin: WOW! GO, FRED!
THAT DID A LOT.
THAT DID A LOT!
WE CAN DREDGE ALL OF THAT NOW,
EVERY BIT OF THAT.
WE'RE IN GOOD SHAPE.
[BLEEP]
WONDERFUL WORK BY FRED.
I DEFINITELY WASN'T GIVING HIM
THE CREDIT HE DESERVED
IN THE BEGINNING.
BUT IT WENT RIGHT TOGETHER.
AND HE DID A DAMN GOOD JOB.
Paul: NO MORE
FIGHTING THE CURRENT.
IT'S GONNA BE A PLEASURE
DIVING IN THIS NOW.
IT'S GONNA BE AWESOME.
**
Fred: TODAY IS MY DAY
IN THE WATER,
AND I'M GOING AFTER
THE GOLD TODAY!
Y'ALL PLAY WITH THE ROCKS.
I'M GOING AFTER THE GOLD, MAN!
LET'S GET OUT THERE AND GET
THAT DREDGE IN THE WATER!
I'M READY!
**
JUST GET THEM WARMED UP.
THAT'S A LOT OF WEIGHT
RIGHT THERE.
IT'S NICE WHEN YOU'RE
ON THE BOTTOM, THOUGH.
WATER LOOKS
PRETTY GOOD TO ME.
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO SEE DOWN
IN SOME OF THE CRACKS
THAT I COULDN'T SEE IN NOW.
HOW'S YOUR AIR?
CHECK YOUR AIR.
Narrator: THE DAKOTA BOYS
HAVE PROVED
THERE'S GOLD
IN THEIR PLUNGE POOL.
NOW, IT'S FRED'S TURN
TO DIVE IN THE SAFE HAVEN
THEY'VE CREATED
BEHIND THEIR DIVERSION.
SAY IT AGAIN.
HE NEEDS ANOTHER WEIGHT BELT...
TO PUT OVER HIS SHOULDER!
YEAH.
HE'S GOT...UGH.
Dustin: YOU WANT MORE WEIGHT?
ALL RIGHT, WHERE YOU WANT IT?
YOU WANT ME TO WRAP IT
AROUND YOUR NECK?
PUT IT ON TOP OF YOUR HEAD?
WHERE DO YOU WANT IT?
WANT ME TO STRAP IT
TO THE FLASHLIGHT?
YOU'RE GONNA PUT A WEIGHT BELT
AROUND YOUR NECK?
Y-YOU HEAR WHAT
YOU'RE SAYING, RIGHT?
OKAY.
Minor: I'M MAKING
ANOTHER WEIGHT BELT,
ABOUT 20 POUNDS.
HEY, IF HE WANTS IT,
HE GETS IT, MAN.
**
Narrator: 72-YEAR-OLD FRED
IS PUTTING HIS NECK ON THE LINE
TO GET TO THE GOLD.
[ AS FRED ]
[ CHUCKLING ]
**
Dustin: THERE WE GO,
A FEW ROCKS.
Narrator: THE CALM WATER CREATED
BY THE NEW DIVERSION
MEANS FRED CAN SUCK UP
MORE RIVER GRAVEL
INTO THE DREDGE
AND THROUGH ITS SLUICE BOX.
THE CREEK'S WATER IS 38 DEGREES,
JUST ABOVE FREEZING.
IF THE DREDGE STOPS
PUMPING HOT WATER
THROUGH HIS WET SUIT,
FRED WOULD DIE
OF HYPOTHERMIA IN MINUTES.
Fred: UGH!
AYE YI YI.
DIVER IS COMING OUT.
AH [BLEEP]
GET THAT --
YEAH, THERE YOU GO.
Dustin: PULL THAT
OFF YOUR FACE.
NEVER MIND. I DON'T WANT
TO RIP YOUR DAMN FACE OFF.
THE WATER JUST GOT
FROZEN DOWN THERE.
WE GOT A HOT ROOM FOR YOU
COMING UP.
MY LEGS ARE SHAKING
RIGHT NOW.
Minor:
YEAH, GET SOME, FRED.
WELL, I CAN HEAR.
Fred: KEPT GETTING COLDER
AND COLDER AND COLDER.
AND, FINALLY,
I JUST WAS SHAKING.
AND I JUST HAD TO COME OUT.
GOOD JOB TODAY, FRED.
YOU WERE DOWN THERE
FOR A LONG TIME.
YOU GOT SOME
BIG-OLD ROCKS OUT NOW.
I'VE GOT TO GO
IN THE HOT ROOM.
OH, IT'S HOT, MAN.
OH, I LOVE IT.
I CAN FEEL IT.
WOO-HOO!
COME ON, HOT ROOM.
OH, IT'S LIKE
A BLAST FURNACE IN HERE.
HE DID IT
WITHOUT HOT WATER.
Paul: YEAH, I THINK
THAT'S THE REASON
WHY FRED WASN'T
GETTING ANY HOT WATER.
OUR LINE --
THE PLASTIC FITTING BROKE
RIGHT IN TWO.
SO IT WASN'T PUMPING
NO HOT WATER IN ON HIM.
I-I SEEN IT SQUIRTING.
BUT I-I JUST THOUGHT
IT WAS JUST A LOOSE FITTING.
I HAD NO IDEA
IT WAS BROKEN.
I DIDN'T EITHER
UNTIL I CAME OVER AND LOOKED.
AND I WAS, LIKE, "OH [BLEEP]
NO WONDER HE HAS NO WATER.
THAT'S WHY HE GOT COLD."
Dustin: FOR WHATEVER REASON,
THEY KEEP BREAKING FROM --
FROM THE VIBRATION...
THIS THING --
THIS THING VIBRATES A LOT, MAN.
-THE VIBRATING IS...
-THIS THING VIBRATES A LOT.
YEAH, AND IT'S JUST
VIBRATING AT THE DUCT.
SO I GUESS THE PLAN IS,
WE'RE GONNA REPLACE
ALL THESE PLASTIC FITTINGS
WITH STEEL FITTINGS.
OH, THERE YOU GO.
NOW LIFT IT.
Minor: THERE'S ALWAYS
A FREAKIN' MALFUNCTION.
MECHANICAL ISSUE AND NATURE
TRYING TO KILL YOU, MAN,
THAT'S NOT A GOOD RECIPE, BRO.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY YOU WOULD
PUT PLASTIC FITTINGS
ON SOMETHING
THAT GETS HOT.
-I DON'T -- I DON'T EITHER.
-IT MAKES NO SENSE.
Wes: NO.
Narrator: IF WES AND PAUL CAN
FIX THE HOT WATER SYSTEM,
THE CREW CAN GET IN
ONE MORE DIVE TODAY.
NO MORE PLASTIC
ON THAT ONE.
THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
Paul: WE REPLACED
THE PLASTIC FITTINGS WITH STEEL.
SO, HOPEFULLY, WE DON'T
BREAK ANY MORE LINES.
I THINK WE'RE READY TO GO.
ALL WE GOT TO DO IS TRY IT OUT.
Narrator: IT'S TIME FOR CARLOS
TO MAKE HIS DEBUT DIVE
AT McKINLEY.
Minor: LAST TIME I DOVE WAS
IN DECEMBER 2015.
UNFORTUNATELY, WE DON'T
GET PAID DEATH PAY HERE.
OR, AT LEAST,
IT WOULDN'T BE MUCH.
Narrator: AFTER SERVING
IN THE MARINE CORPS,
CARLOS SPENT 13 YEARS DIVING
IN THE GULF OF MEXICO.
MOMENT OF TRUTH, AMIGO!
MOMENT OF TRUTH IS
RIGHT UPON US.
IT'S TIME TO MAKE PEACE
WITH THIS LADY.
BUT HE'S NEVER MINED FOR GOLD
IN A FREEZING,
FAST-FLOWING CREEK.
Minor: IF I WALK OUT
OF THAT WATER...BREATHING,
WITH ALL MY FINGERS INTACT,
I THINK I WILL CALL THAT
FOR A SUCCESS.
BUT I HAVE NO IDEA
HOW I GOT MYSELF
INTO THIS KIND OF STUFF, MAN.
Dustin: WHAT YOU'RE GONNA DO
IS A LOT OF WORK, MAN.
START THIS.
FOLLOW THE WALL.
AND THEN I WANT YOU TAKE
ALL THAT OUT, TOO.
I REALLY WANT TO SEE A HUGE
DAMN HOLE HERE, ALL RIGHT?
-GOT YOU, MAN.
-JUST TAKE AS MUCH AS YOU CAN.
Dustin: HOW WE DOING?
Wes: IT'S BARELY WARM.
IT'S STARTING TO GET THERE.
IT'S JUST ENGINES
TAKE A WHILE TO WARM UP.
THEY -- THEY'RE TINY.
WOO, THAT'S HOT! HOLD ON.
IT'S HOT AS [BLEEP]
WE'LL GET YOU IN THERE.
YOU TAKE A LITTLE BIT
OF TRIAL AND ERROR HERE, BUDDY.
FEELING GOOD?
OKAY.
LET'S GO SWIMMING.
Minor: DIVER IN THE WATER.
AHH!
HEY, CARLOS,
THAT WATER'S NOT LIKE
THE GULF OF MEXICO,
IS IT?
NO! THIS IS NOTHING
LIKE THE GULF OF MEXICO.
IT'S ABOUT 80 DEGREES
IN THE GULF OF MEXICO.
OH, YEAH.
I MEAN.
IT'S WARM WHEN IT'S 40 HERE.
WELL, HOW DOES IT FEEL
DOWN THERE?
**
Fred: GIVE IT HELL.
WE WANT TO SEE SOME --
WE WANT TO SEE SOME ROCKS
COMING OUTTA THAT SLUICE BOX.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY
ABOUT BEGINNER'S LUCK, MAN.
FIRST TIME
ON THE DREDGE,
OH, BRING OUT A NUGGET
OUT OF THERE.
THE SLUICE LOOKS
REALLY GOOD.
IT LOOKS LIKE EVERYTHING
IS ROLLING PERFECT.
WOO! HE'S DIGGING, MAN.
THIS IS A GREAT DAY FOR ME.
WE'RE MOVING YARDAGE.
I THINK WE'RE GONNA
GET GOLD OUT OF THIS STUFF.
Fred: COMING ON UP.
SET THE DREDGE OFF
TO THE SIDE THERE.
AHH.
HE'S BEEN DOWN A COUPLE HOURS
AND...LOOKING GOOD, MAN!
-GOOD TIMES?
-GET PUMPED.
ALL RIGHT.
GOOD JOB, MAN. GOOD JOB.
Minor: AND I WAS RIGHT NEXT
TO THE DIVERSION.
YOU CAN SEE
THE DIFFERENCE OF WATER,
THIS BEING VERY NICE
AND THAT OTHER SIDE
OF THAT FREAKIN' DIVERSION.
I CAN PUT MY HANDS
UNDERNEATH AND ALL THAT,
AND IT WANTS TO RIP IT OFF.
AWESOME, MAN.
WE MOVED SOME DIRT TODAY.
YEAH.
TOLD YOU, MAN, 100%.
MADE FRIENDS
WITH THIS [BLEEP] DAMN CREEK.
HOPEFULLY, I'LL LIKE IT
FOR A LITTLE BIT LONGER.
**
Paul: WE'RE GONNA PULL
ALL THESE MATS OUT NOW,
CLEAN THEM OUT,
SEE WHAT WE COME UP WITH.
I THINK WE DID
PRETTY GOOD ON THIS ONE.
LOVE TO GET SOME GOLD.
Fred: REALLY HOPEFUL
THAT WE'RE GONNA SEE SOME
CLINKERS COMING OUT OF THERE,
NOT THEM LITTLE,
PING, PING, PING,
BUT CLANK, CLANK, CLANK.
**
LOOKING GOOD.
I KNOW THEY SURE SMELL GOOD.
GOOD, FRESH, HOT BURGERS --
NOTHING BETTER THAN THAT
WHEN YOU GET OUT OF COLD WATER.
WE'RE GONNA PLAY A LITTLE JOKE
ON DUSTIN HERE.
HE'S DOWN THERE DIVING.
I KNOW HE'S GETTING HUNGRY.
SMELL ANYTHING?
GETTING HUNGRY ANY TIME SOON?
WE'RE LITERALLY HOLDING
A BURGER, MAN,
RIGHT ON YOUR INTAKE.
[ LAUGHING ]
THAT'S GOOD.
**
Paul: THIS IS
THE MONEY TRAY, RIGHT HERE.
Dustin: THINK SO?
Paul: THERE'S GOLD.
I TELL YOU! THERE'S GOLD!
Narrator: THE DAKOTA BOYS
ARE HUNTING
FOR A LIFE-CHANGING
FORTUNE IN GOLD,
HIDDEN BENEATH THE RAGING WATERS
OF McKINLEY CREEK.
THANK YOU, SIR.
I DON'T CARE
IF IT'S BIG OR LITTLE
OR IT'S FINE DUST
OR IT'S GIANT NUGGETS.
I WANT A LOT OF GOLD.
TECHNICAL PROBLEMS MEAN
THEY'VE ONLY MANAGED
TO MINE FOR 6 HOURS.
Wes: YOU KNOW, A LOT OF TIMES,
WE CAN'T SEE HALF OF THE GOLD
THAT'S IN THERE.
WE'LL FIND OUT HERE QUICK.
I GOT TO TELL YOU,
THERE'S ONLY A FEW FLAKES.
I HAVEN'T SEEN
ANYTHING ELSE.
FEELS LIGHT COMPARED
TO CARRYING ROCK.
Fred: HEY,
WHAT YOU GOT THERE, MAN?
SPECIAL DELIVERY.
WE GOT SOME PAY DIRT.
WE'LL PROCESS ALL THAT.
AND WE'LL FIND OUT --
WE'LL FIND OUT HERE, SHORTLY.
Narrator: THE MINI TROMMEL WAS
DESIGNED BY WES AND PAUL
TO REPLACE THE SLOW PROCESS
OF HAND-PANNING
THE CONCENTRATE FOR GOLD.
Wes: WHAT THIS TROMMEL DOES IS,
WHEN I DROP MATERIAL IN IT,
IT GOES THROUGH A CLASSIFYING
SCREEN ON THE INSIDE,
DROPS OUT
INTO ARCHIMEDES' SCREW.
AND IT CLIMBS THE GOLD BACK UP
AND DROPS IT OUT
INTO OUR SLUICE BOX.
THIS IS GONNA SEPARATE THE GOLD
FROM THE HEAVY STUFF.
Dustin: EVERY DAY THAT YOU DIG,
YOU'RE HOPING TO GET GOLD,
HAS TO PAY OFF.
WHAT THE HELL ARE WE DOING HERE
IF IT DOESN'T PAY OFF?
Wes: LOOK AT THAT PIECE OF GOLD
RIGHT THERE ALREADY.
CAN YOU SEE THAT PIECE
RIGHT THERE?
Fred: YEP.
WELL, WHEN YOU CAN SEE IT,
THAT'S GOOD.
Wes: THIS IS WHAT
IT'S ALL ABOUT RIGHT HERE.
THAT --
THAT IS REALLY GREAT.
THAT NUGGET THAT YOU FOUND
IN THERE, HOW BIG WAS IT?
IT'S A LITTLE-BITTY
OLD PICKER,
AIN'T NOTHING LIKE
WHAT WE FOUND LAST TIME.
BUT STILL, YOU KNOW,
IF YOU CAN PICK THEM UP,
THEY CALL THEM A PICKER.
GOTCHA --
"A PICKER."
NOW, I'M CURIOUS TO SEE
WHAT HE'S GOT.
IT'S HEADED ON UP.
Fred: REMEMBER, WE'VE ONLY DONE
ABOUT 15 YARDS OF MATERIAL.
THAT IS A BADASS
LITTLE NUGGET, HUH?
Paul: THAT'S PRETTY IMPRESSIVE
FOR THE AMOUNT OF DIRT
WE'VE ACTUALLY RUN.
-YEAH, IT IS.
IF YOU THINK
ABOUT THAT, THAT'S ALMOST --
THAT'S CLOSE TO A HALF OUNCE
OF GOLD RIGHT THERE.
Wes: YEAH,
THAT'S SOME NICE GOLD.
Narrator: HALF AN OUNCE
IS WORTH JUST $600.
BUT FINDING GOLD SO EARLY
IS A SIGN
THAT THEY COULD BE RIGHT ABOVE
A DEPOSIT WORTH MILLIONS.
SITTING GOOD.
WE'VE ONLY BEEN
IN THE WATER
FOR JUST A LIMITED
NUMBER OF HOURS
AND WE GOT OUR FIRST
HALF OUNCE OF GOLD.
IF WE'RE GETTING
THAT OUT OF THE TOP,
NEXT WEEK
MIGHT BE EVEN BETTER.
IT MIGHT BE DOUBLE
WHAT WE GOT HERE.
WE NEED TO GET PAID.
JUST GOT TO FIND THAT ONE POCKET
THAT'S GOT THE PILE OF IT.
WE'RE JUST
GETTING STARTED, MAN.
TO ME, THAT IS ONE HELL
OF A GOOD SIGN.
NEXT CLEAN-OUT,
WE'RE GONNA HAVE 4 OUNCES,
PLUS THAT.
SIX OUNCES.
I'M GONNA FIND SOME CLINKERS,
MAN, THAT DROP IN THERE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
THEY'RE GONNA COUNT, MAN.
I'M GOING AFTER
THE BIG STUFF.
Minor:
EVERY SPECK COUNTS, HUH?
YEP, LET'S BOTTLE
THIS STUFF UP, MAN.
-ALL RIGHT.
-WOW, THAT WAS PRETTY GOOD.
**
I'D LIKE TO SEE
ABOUT 200 TO 300 OUNCES.
ABOUT 200 OUNCES IS
WHAT MY HOPES AND DREAMS ARE.
I MEAN, WITH THE LITTLE BIT
OF MATERIAL THAT WE'VE RUN
AND THE AMOUNT OF GOLD
THAT WE'VE FOUND SO FAR,
THE WAY IT'S LOOKING,
I'M GONNA SAY 1,000 OUNCES.
**
Fred: IF WE CAN FIND
A QUARTER-OUNCE NUGGET
IN THE FIRST
4 FEET OF MATERIAL,
THAT MEANS THERE MAY BE
A WHOLE LOT
MORE OF THOSE THINGS,
EVEN BIGGER,
A LITTLE LOWER DOWN IN THERE.
I THINK MOTHER NATURE HAS
LEFT US SOME GOOD GOLD TO FIND.
Narrator: ON THE NEXT EPISODE...
I WANTED
TO PICK UP MY GOLD.
WE DON'T HAVE
ANY GOLD FOR YOU RIGHT NOW.
BE HONEST -- IS THERE GOLD
ON THIS CREEK OR NOT?!
[ GROANING ]
[BLEEP]
GET THAT DAMN THING
OFF YOUR BACK!
[ CHUCKLING ]
I THINK THAT GENERATOR
IS ABOUT TO BLOW!
HEY, THE WINCH IS ON FIRE!
THAT'S A BAD SITUATION
RIGHT THERE, MAN!