GON' BE A GOOD DAY!
Dustin: THANK YOU.
READY?
Paul:
COMING DOWN.
Dustin: WE'LL FIND OUT
WHAT THIS THING'S MADE OF.
Fred:
ALL RIGHT, COMING UP.
OH, MY GOD! LOOK AT THAT!
Paul: THAT'S [BLEEP]
SWEET, DUDE!
YEAH!
Carlos:
THAT THERE IS A SUCCESSFUL TEST.
Man: HELL, YEAH.
LET'S SEE IF WE GOT ANY...
[ LINE SNAPS,
THUMP ]
[BLEEP]
Dustin:
GET HIM OUTTA THERE.
FRED!
Dustin: I NEED SOMEBODY
TO CHECK OUT THE GRABOID.
IF THAT THING CAN WORK,
I'LL MAKE IT WORK.
I ALSO NEED SOMEBODY
TO GO DOWN
AND USE THIS THING
THAT CAN'T SUE ME.
SLIPPERY AS HELL!
Paul: TAKE IT EASY!
Dustin: THAT'S WHY THEY CALL
THEM ACCIDENTS, HUH?
THAT'S A BEAUTIFUL NUGGET.
THE GOLD
IS GETTING BETTER.
Carlos: [BLEEP]
IT'S GETTING BETTER, MAN!
WE'RE GETTING A LOT
CLOSER TO THAT BOTTOM.
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
DISCOVERY COMMUNICATIONS
Fred:
WE'RE KINDA HOPING THAT BEDROCK
IS BETWEEN 15 AND 20 FEET.
SO, WE'RE GETTING DOWN THERE.
WHAT IT DOES, IT --
UH, BEDROCK KINDA BELLIES OUT
LIKE THAT SOME WAY
OR ANOTHER.
WE DON'T KNOW.
AND, HOPEFULLY,
DUSTIN'LL TRY
TO GET DOWN THERE,
JUST FOLLOW IT
ALL ON DOWN.
AND THERE'LL BE A WHOLE WALL,
THEN, OF ROCKS.
AND WE START JUST BRINGING
THAT STUFF BEHIND US
AND, UH, GETTING DOWN AS FAR
AS WE CAN ON THAT BEDROCK.
COME OUT TOWARD THE CREEK
WITH A LITTLE BIT MORE,
KEEP COMING UP TOWARD
THE [INDISTINCT].
WE'RE GONNA FIND GOLD!
WE ARE HOPEFUL
THAT, THIS WEEK,
WE WILL FIND BEDROCK.
Narrator:
HIGH IN THE CHILKAT MOUNTAINS
OF SOUTHEAST ALASKA,
THE DAKOTA BOYS ARE SEARCHING
FOR A LIFE-CHANGING
DEPOSIT OF GOLD.
START IT UP!
Dustin: ALL RIGHT.
YOU READY, BOBBY?
EACH CREW MEMBER
IS ON A SHARE.
BUT, JUST TO COVER
THEIR RUNNING COSTS,
THEY NEED $50,000
WORTH OF GOLD.
WINTER IS FAST APPROACHING.
AND THEY'RE IN A RACE
TO STRIKE IT RICH.
EVERYBODY LOVES
TO SEE GOLD.
I THINK EVEN CARLOS
WOULD LOVE TO SEE GOLD.
I JUST WANNA BE THE ONE
TO FIND IT, MAN!
WOO!
BETTER HOPE I BREAK MY LEG
OR SOMETHING
'CAUSE THAT'S THE ONLY WAY
YOU'RE STOPPING ME TODAY.
Narrator: JUST DAYS AGO,
CARLOS DREDGED DOWN
6 FEET IN THIS SPOT
AND FOUND HIS FIRST GOLD.
THEY ARE CLOSER THAN EVER
TO A MASSIVE PAYDAY.
Justin:
OH, [BLEEP] DAMN!
Fred: HEY, DON'T BE A WUSSY!
WE GOT TO THE POINT
WHERE WE HIT WHITE WATER, MAN.
SO WE'LL HAVE
TO DOUBLE THE WEIGHT.
EVEN THOUGH HE'S GOT
A HEAVY WEIGHT BELT ON,
THAT'S GONNA WHIP HIM
AROUND QUITE A BIT.
[BLEEP] DAMN!
I WANNA SEE SOME GOLD
IN THAT BOX.
ARE YOU READY
FOR THIS TODAY?
I WISH YOU GOOD LUCK,
GOOD HUNTING, AND GOLD.
LET'S GO!
LOOKING GOOD BACK THERE,
REALLY GOOD.
Narrator: TEN FEET BELOW
THE SURFACE OF THE CREEK,
DUSTIN IS DREDGING IN
A STEEP-SIDED HOLE,
SUCKING UP ROCKS AND GRAVEL
TO GET DOWN TO THE GOLD
HE BELIEVES LIES ON BEDROCK.
Fred: HEY, YA' GOTTA BE CAREFUL
WITH THEM THINGS! [ Laughs ]
WHAT I ALWAYS DO.
GOTTA KNOW WHAT
MY SURROUNDINGS ARE FIRST.
OKAY.
WHOA!
AW, [BLEEP]!
DUSTIN!
WHERE YOU AT?
Paul:
IS HE ALL RIGHT?
Fred:
DUSTIN! WHERE YOU AT?
HEY, BRING HIM UP!
OH, [BLEEP].
YEAH, YEAH.
TIME TO TAKE A BREAK, MAN.
Richardson:
YOU ALL RIGHT?
OH, [BLEEP] HE'S
ALL WRAPPED UP, TOO!
YEAH, HE'S ALL TWISTED.
HOLY [BLEEP],
THAT WAS A CLOSE CALL.
EASY, EASY.
Carlos:
HOLD ON, HOLD ON. WE'LL DO
THAT ONE EASY, EASY, EASY.
MINERAL WATER.
THERE YOU GO.
IT GOT ME, MAN.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW BAD IT GOT ME.
THAT'S A WAKE-UP
CALL, BROTHER.
Paul: GET A CLOSER LOOK
ANYWAYS, RIGHT?
OOH, IT IS TENDER.
I GOT HIT.
THAT'S GONNA BE SORE, SORE.
MY WHOLE ARM HURTS.
SCARED THE HELL OUT OF ME,
IS WHAT JUST HAPPENED.
A ROCK CAME DOWN
AND GOT ME.
IT HURT LIKE HELL.
AND, UH, BIG
WAKE-UP CALL THERE.
YOU THINK IT'S FRACTURED?
IT'S JUST A HURT MUSCLE.
IT'S STIFFENING UP ON ME.
YEAH, BUT YOU'RE
TALKING IN 2 OR 300 --
COUPLE HUNDRED POUNDS
FALLING DOWN OFF...
IT'S JUST
MY LITTLE FINGERS.
GROUP HUG?
NO, NO. TWO-SECOND HUG.
TWO SECONDS...
WHAT THE [BLEEP], MAN?
IT -- IT HELPS, DUDE.
[ LAUGHING ]
THANKS, CARLOS.
Richardson: WHAT HAPPENED?
Carlos: IT HELPS, RIGHT?
I'M TELLING YOU.
IT'S CHICKEN
OF THE SOUP, BRO.
CHICKEN OF THE SOUL
OR SOUP OF THE SOUL,
WHATEVER THAT [BLEEP].
YEAH, IT DOES.
IT WORKS. I KNOW.
I'VE BEEN IN
THAT SITUATION.
HE'S FEELING MY PAIN,
APPARENTLY.
OH, GOD.
WHAT A ROUGH DAY.
Fred: IT -- IT WAS SCARY.
I KNOW IT WAS SCARY FOR HIM.
THIS IS KIND OF
A GRIM REMINDER
THAT, UH, THIS CREEK
IS DANGEROUS OUT HERE.
YOU'VE GOT TO BE
ON YOUR TOES AT ALL TIMES.
BUT WE ARE REALLY
PUSHING THE LIMIT RIGHT NOW
ON WHAT YOU CAN DO.
YOU CAN BET THAT.
IT IS DANGEROUS DOWN THERE.
NOBODY SHOULD BE DOWN THERE.
IF ANYBODY'S GOING BACK
IN THAT HOLE, IT'S ME.
I, UH, I'M GONNA JUMP IN.
UH, I CAN'T LET THIS DAY
GO TO WASTE.
IT'S NOT THE SAFEST THING TO DO.
BUT I JUST -- I'M --
I'M GETTING ANXIOUS.
THIS COULD BE THE LAST CHANCE
TO GET GOLD.
HE NEEDS
TO RESPECT THE CREEK.
BECAUSE, IF YOU DON'T
RESPECT THIS CREEK, MAN,
IT'LL BITE YOU IN THE ASS
AT THE END, BROTHER.
Narrator: THE LARGE BOULDER
THAT HIT DUSTIN
HAS FALLEN INTO THE HOLE,
BLOCKING HIS PATH
TO THE GOLD.
Fred: ALL RIGHT. UH, THE CLAW
IS COMING DOWN THE WALL
RIGHT IN FRONT OF THE DIVE
STATION RIGHT NOW.
TRYING TO POSITION IT
SO IT STAYS IN THE CLAW.
AND HE'S, UH,
TRYING TO MAKE SURE
THAT IT WON'T FALL OUT.
YEP.
OKAY,
WHAT DO YOU NEED?
IT'S COMING UP.
COMING UP.
ROGER.
ALL RIGHT.
LOOKS LIKE IT'S HOLDING.
NOPE, IT CAME OFF.
[ GROANS ]
I THINK IF THE, UH,
ROCK IS REALLY, REALLY ROUND,
AND, UH, THOSE ROUND ROCKS
JUST DON'T HAVE
ANY HANDLES ON 'EM.
Narrator:
DUSTIN CAN'T GET THE CLAW
TO HOOK BEHIND
THE MASSIVE ROCK.
SO, WHAT'S
YOUR GAME PLAN?
JUST THE CABLE BY ITSELF?
OKAY, COPY THAT.
'KAY. I'M SENDING THE, UH,
SHACKLE DOWN TO YOU.
Carlos: COME ON, MAN!
THIS'LL WORK!
COME ON! COME ON!
ALL RIGHT. TAKE THIS.
OKAY.
COME ON!
[BLEEP] DAMN IT!
[BLEEP]
ALL RIGHT, [BLEEP]
THIS [BLEEP].
DONE WITH THIS.
IT'S SO BIG
AND SO ROUND,
SO SMOOTH THAT IT --
IT'S A PAIN.
IT'S A PAIN BECAUSE
THAT MAKES YOU
JUST WANNA JUST
EITHER GO CRAZY
OR JUST END
THE DIVE, YOU KNOW?
THAT ONE SINGLE BOULDER
GOT INSIDE MY HEAD.
HOW BIG'S THAT [BLEEP], MAN?
'BOUT THAT BIG.
THAT BIG?
HOLY [BLEEP]!
I LET ONE BOULDER BEAT ME.
IT JUST ATE MY BREAKFAST.
Narrator:
IF THEY CAN'T MOVE THE BOULDER,
THEY CAN'T GET TO THE GOLD.
WHEW!
STAND OVER HERE
FOR A LITTLE BIT.
WE GOTTA HAVE SOMETHING
BETTER TO GRAB THEM ROCKS
AND PICK 'EM
AND PULL 'EM OUT.
I JUST FEEL LIKE
THIS IS CAVEMAN STUFF.
WE GOTTA SET
SOMETHING UP BETTER.
TOUGH DAY AT THE OFFICE
WHEN YOU CAN'T MOVE A BOULDER.
MY HAND IS ABSOLUTELY NUMB.
Fred:
BUT THERE'S A REASONABLE AMOUNT
OF TIME YOU CAN SPEND
ON A CERTAIN TASK.
WASTED A WHOLE HOUR OF TIME
PULLING ON ONE DAMN ROCK.
I'M RUNNING OUTTA TIME.
WE'VE GOTTA GET
A BETTER SOLUTION FOR THIS.
Narrator: UP AHEAD...
IT WON'T GO.
Dustin:
CLICK ON IT SOME MORE.
YEAH. UP.
UP.
[BLEEP]
HEY, FELLAS!
CHECK IT OUT!
WHAT YOU GOT?
I GOT SOME FUN TOYS!
Narrator: DUSTIN HAS RETURNED
FROM TOWN WITH A DEVICE
THAT COULD SOLVE
HIS BOULDER PROBLEM.
LOOK AT THIS THING.
THAT LOOKS PRETTY
GOD DANG NICE.
I KNOW MONEY'S TIGHT RIGHT NOW.
BUT I HAD TO DO IT.
WE SPENT $3,500
ON THIS ROCK LIFT.
AND, UH, I THINK
WHAT IT'S GONNA DO
IS IT'S GONNA SPEED UP
MY PROCESS SO MUCH
THAT WE WON'T EVEN
BLINK AT THAT $3,500.
Fred:
LOOKS LIKE HELL, DON'T IT?
CALLING IT A GRABOID?
YOU KNOW THE LITTLE MACHINES
THAT PULL UP TEDDY BEARS?
MM-HMM.
YEAH, YEAH.
IT'S MADE SPECIFICALLY
FOR LIFTING UP ROCKS.
I WAS WATCHING YOU GUYS
THE OTHER DAY.
AND -- AND THE CABLE
JUST KEPT SLIPPING OFF
AND SLIPPING OFF.
AND, UH, THIS WILL HELP US
GET THOSE ROCKS OUTTA THERE
QUICKLY AND EFFICIENCY.
Narrator: DUSTIN'S GRABOID
IS MADE UP OF THREE
TONGS CONNECTED TOGETHER
BY A COLLAR AT THE TOP.
AS THE COLLAR IS RAISED,
THE TONGS PIVOT AND CLOSE
AROUND THE ROCK.
THE INGENIOUS THING ABOUT
THE PIVOT MECHANISM IS THAT,
THE HEAVIER THE ROCK,
THE STRONGER THE GRIP.
WOW. WELL, THESE ARE
THE JAWS, OBVIOUSLY.
LOOKS LIKE IT'S GONNA
WORK FOR ME.
IT'S GOT A 30-INCH
GRIP ON IT.
SO WE CAN GRAB UP
TO 30-INCH ROCKS.
IT'LL SPEED UP MY PROCESS.
HOPEFULLY, THIS IS THE ANSWER
TO ALL OUR STRUGGLES UNDERWATER.
YEAH, IF I CAN GET THAT
PIECE OF TRASH ROCK OUT.
TO GET ONE ROCK OUT.
WE GOTTA GO SET UP SOME
SERIOUS ANCHORS FOR THIS THING.
Y'ALL READY? Y'ALL WITH ME?
YUP.
'KAY. LET'S DO IT.
GO GET SUITED UP.
Narrator: COUPLED WITH THE COST
OF THE HELICOPTER LIFT
TO GET THE GRABOID TO SITE,
DUSTIN'S NEW DEVICE
HAS SET THEM BACK $5,000,
ALMOST THE LAST
OF THEIR CASH.
I got it.
Dustin:
GRABOID'S COMING IN.
Carlos:
RIGHT OVER US.
THAT WAS
PRETTY QUICK!
WHOO!
WHOO-HOO!
NAILED IT!
Narrator: THE GRABOID WEIGHS
170 POUNDS
AND ALSO NEEDS 400 POUNDS
OF GEAR TO RIG IT.
[BLEEP] DANG, DUDE!
Dustin: 'CROSS THE CREEK,
WE'RE GONNA HAVE THIS ONE LINE
COME INTO RIGHT HERE.
HARD ANCHOR POINTS
ON EITHER END.
ON THAT CABLE,
IT'S GONNA GO STRAIGHT DOWN.
THERE'S A BIG ROCK DOWNSTREAM
RIGHT THERE THAT
WE'RE GONNA HOOK THAT TO.
AND, HOPEFULLY, IT'S A LOT
CLEANER AND STRONGER.
Narrator: DUSTIN'S PLAN --
FIRST ATTACH A SUPPORT CABLE
ACROSS THE CREEK.
NEXT, RUN THE TRANSPORT CABLE
OVER THE DIVE SITE,
75 FEET DOWNSTREAM
TO AN ANCHOR POINT.
THE GRABOID CAN THEN LIFT
BOULDERS AND DUMP THEM
CLEAR OF THE DIVE SITE.
Dustin: I DON'T SEE
MYSELF GOING DOWN.
BUT THAT'S WHY THEY
CALL 'EM ACCIDENTS, HUH?
THIRTY FEET ABOVE THE BRIDGE,
THE ONLY WAY DUSTIN
CAN GET TO THE FAR SIDE
TO FIX ANCHOR POINTS
IS BY WADING THROUGH
THE GLACIAL WHITE WATER.
BE CAREFUL, MAN.
Dustin: I JUST NEED A STICK.
THAT MIGHT BE EASIER.
THERE'S A HUGE CHANCE
THAT I'M GONNA GET WET BAD!
THIS IS CRAZY, DUDE.
I'M INSANE.
STEP ONE.
TO MAKE HOLES
IN THE WALL BIG ENOUGH
FOR HIS 3-FOOT ANCHOR BOLTS,
DUSTIN HAS TO USE A CORE DRILL.
IF WE'RE GONNA LIFT UP
2,000-POUND ROCKS
AND IT'S GONNA BE OVER MY HEAD,
I'MA MAKE IT STRONG.
I'MA MAKE IT REAL STRONG.
Richardson: IN
THERE PRETTY GOOD.
YEAH, I'M
HAPPY WITH THAT.
TWO IS GONNA BE
ENOUGH, RIGHT?
YES. IT'S PROBABLY
OVERKILL BUT YEAH.
I'M FINE WITH OVERKILL.
I UNDERSTAND.
CONCRETE THESE THINGS IN,
MAKE 'EM RIGHT.
WE'VE GOT THESE LONG
ANCHOR BOLTS.
I'M JUST EPOXYING THESE
INTO THESE, UH,
THE HOLES THAT DUSTIN BORED.
WE'RE GOING EXTRA
STRONG ON THESE.
ONCE THAT, UH,
ONCE THAT STUFF SETS,
THESE SHOULD BE ANCHORED
IN AS STRONG AS THE ROCK ITSELF.
Fred:
I HAVE NO DOUBT IT'LL HOLD.
PUT SOME GOOD ANCHORS
IN OVER THERE.
GOOD, STRONG CABLE
WAY UP TOP,
IT LOOKS LIKE THE SYSTEM
WE SHOULD'VE STARTED WITH.
WOO!
WOW.
GOOD JOB THERE,
DUSTIN.
USE THE WEBBING.
WHEN IT PULLS, IT PULLS
ON ALL THREE ANCHORS
AT THE SAME EXACT TIME
AND THE SAME EXACT WEIGHT.
I'MA SET IT UP SO STRONG
THAT THING'LL NEVER POP.
IT'S GETTING COLD HERE.
THE END OF
THE SEASON'S HAPPENING.
WE JUST NEED THIS
TO GET DONE.
OTHERWISE, I'M NOT GONNA
FINISH THIS DAMN HOLE.
WE WON'T HAVE ANY GOLD
AT THE END OF THE SEASON.
Richardson:
THAT'LL WORK.
WE'VE GOT THIS LARGE PULLEY
THAT'S GOING ONTO THIS CABLE.
ONCE I GET THIS HOOKED UP, WE'RE
GONNA GET IT OUT TO THE MIDDLE.
READY?
YEAH!
OH, YEAH.
GONNA SEND
A CABLE DOWNSTREAM.
SO WE'RE HOPING WE GOT
ENOUGH STRETCH AND HEIGHT.
GOT IT!
OKAY.
Narrator: THE CREW HAS BOTH
THE CROSS-CREEK
AND DOWNSTREAM CABLES RIGGED.
LOOKING AT THAT DISTANCE,
I THINK IT'S GONNA
WORK JUST FINE.
GOT OUR COME-ALONG ATTACHED TO
A, UH, CABLE PULLER OUT THERE.
SEE IF WE CAN'T
PULL THIS THING TIGHTER.
NOW WATCH.
IF THAT [BLEEP] COMES LOOSE,
YOU'RE IN A BAD SPOT,
JUST SO YOU KNOW.
MAN, WE GOT A LOT OF --
A LOT OF TENSION HERE.
A LOT.
Narrator: THE 75-FOOT CABLE
HAS TO BE TIGHT ENOUGH
TO SUPPORT THE WEIGHT
OF THE GRABOID
AND A GIANT BOULDER.
THAT'S STARTING
TO GET SCARY TIGHT.
LOOKING GOOD TO ME!
I DON'T THINK
IT'S TIGHT ENOUGH.
AND IN MY HEAD,
THAT HAS TO BE
DANGEROUSLY TIGHT IN ORDER
TO PICK UP STUFF.
IT'S GETTING THERE.
IT WON'T GO.
CLICK ON IT SOME MORE.
YEAH. YEAH. COME UP.
UP.
WHY CAN'T WE JUST [BLEEP]
DO THINGS RIGHT?
[BLEEP]
IT WON'T GO.
CLICK ON IT SOME MORE.
OH, [BLEEP].
THAT WAS MORE VIOLENT
THAN I EXPECTED.
Narrator:
WINTER IS THREATENING TO SHUT
THE DAKOTA BOYS DOWN ANY DAY.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THEY JUST DID.
BUT IT MADE
THE WHOLE CABLE JUMP.
Narrator: THEY'VE SPENT ALMOST
THE LAST OF THEIR CASH
ON A NEW CABLE SYSTEM
TO REMOVE THE BOULDER
THAT'S BLOCKING THEM
FROM THE GOAL.
WE WOULD'VE THOUGHT WE WOULDA
HAD THIS ALL FIXED BY NOW.
BUT, UH, APPARENTLY,
UH, APPARENTLY,
WE DON'T HAVE IT FIXED.
Narrator:
DUSTIN HAS TO FIX THE CLAMP
AND RETENTION THE CABLE.
Dustin:
HOW COME I'M ALWAYS OUT HERE?
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT'S LEARNING
TO CLIMB AND [BLEEP].
THIS IS A FRICTION DEVICE
THAT GRABS AHOLD OF THE CABLE
WHILE YOU PULL IT TIGHT.
RIGHT NOW, IT'S NOT GRABBING.
I'M TRYING TO PUT
A BUNCHA JUNK IN THE WAY.
SO, HOPEFULLY,
THIS THING WILL GRIP.
SO, DUCT TAPE AND ZIP TIES.
WE'RE GONNA TRY
THIS [BLEEP].
I AIN'T [BLEEP] AROUND.
WE DOING IT.
WHEN YOUR GREAT EQUIPMENT
DOESN'T WORK,
YOU HAVE TO GHETTO-FY IT.
GOTTA MODIFY IT?
IT'S TIME TO MODIFY!
ALL RIGHT. [BLEEP]
TRY IT AGAIN, MAN.
IS THAT GONNA HOLD?
LITTLE DUCT TAPE,
NO BIG DEAL?
SEEMS TO BE SO FAR.
TRICK IS TO GO A QUARTER
TURN BEFORE IT BREAKS.
YEAH, WHAT'S THAT?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
I GUESS, IF IT BREAKS, WE'LL
BACK IT OFF A QUARTER TURN.
THINK WE GOT IT?
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
HOPEFULLY WE GOT
OUR CABLE TIGHT ENOUGH.
ALL RIGHT. THIS IS ONLY
SUPPOSED TO TAKE,
LIKE, 20 MINUTES, DUDE.
Narrator:
THE CABLE FINALLY INSTALLED,
THE CREW HEADS HOME
FOR THE NIGHT.
Fred: GOOD RIDE.
LOOKING FORWARD TO GETTING
IN THE WATER TODAY.
TODAY IS A BIG DAY.
WHEN YOU FIRST
PUT STUFF TOGETHER,
THINGS DON'T
ALWAYS WORK RIGHT.
SO, UH, WE'RE HOPING
FOR THE BEST.
Dustin: WE GOT THE CABLES
TENSIONED PERFECT.
THE HOIST IS ON.
NOW WE'RE GONNA DO
SOME TESTS TO FIND OUT
WHAT THIS THING IS MADE OF.
I'M DEFINITELY LOOKING FORWARD
TO SEEING THIS THING IN ACTION.
THAT IS ONE AWKWARD SON
OF A [BLEEP].
COMING UP?
YEAH.
COMING UP.
LET'S SEE IF
I CAN GET IT TO OPEN.
Carlos: READY?
[ GRUNTS ]
NOPE.
Dustin: THE BOLT'S TOO TIGHT.
[BLEEP] WON'T OPEN UP.
Fred: I GOT IT.
GIMME A LITTLE, UH,
PRESSING ON IT.
LET'S GO TOGETHER.
WEE-HEE-HOO!
THAT'S A BAD,
BAD MAN RIGHT THERE.
Narrator:
DUSTIN AND THE CREW ARE READY
TO DEPLOY THE GRABOID.
FRED IS IMPATIENT
TO KEEP DREDGING.
I'M GONNA GO AHEAD
AND DO SOME DIVING TODAY,
SEE IF WE GET
A LITTLE BIT DONE.
I'VE ONLY GOT A LIMITED
NUMBER OF DIVES LEFT.
I, UH, I'M A LITTLE FRUSTRATED
WITH THAT, I GOTTA ADMIT.
I WANT SOME PROGRESS.
UH, I WANT SOME RESULTS.
Dustin: WHAT ARE
YOU THINKING, FRED?
ALL RIGHT.
GOTTA HAVE THAT TURN.
THAT'LL WORK.
YEAH.
IT'LL BE A GOOD DAY.
Narrator:
UNTIL THEY CLEAR THE BOULDER,
FRED CAN ONLY DREDGE
LOW-GRADE MATERIAL
IN THE DOWNSTREAM
PART OF THE POOL.
Carlos: ALL RIGHT, FRED.
I'VE GOT YOU ON COMMS.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
I JUST GONNA DREDGE
STRAIGHT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT. YOU'RE READY
TO ROCK AND ROLL, FRED.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, FRED.
I MEAN, GONNA GIVE YOU
[BLEEP] GOOD JOB.
WE'VE GOTTEN A LOT
OF GOOD MATERIAL OUT.
SO I GUESS THE NEXT STEP
IS TO FIND THAT GOLD.
THIS IS OUR FIRST SHOT AT IT.
DON'T STAND UNDER IT!
Narrator:
FOR THE FIRST RUN,
THE CREW TESTS THE GRABOID
WITH A SURFACE ROCK.
HOW 'BOUT THAT BIG ONE
RIGHT THERE?
YEAH, THAT ONE.
THIS ONE?
YEAH.
WELL, WE GOT A REAL
WEIRD-SHAPED ROCK.
SO, IF WE CAN'T PICK IT UP
WITH THIS, UH, GRABOID,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT GOOD
IT'S GONNA DO US.
TRY THAT.
YEAH! THAT'S HOW
IT'S SUPPOSED TO WORK!
PRETTY GOOD-SIZED
ONE, TOO.
[BLEEP] YEAH!
WOO!
FINALLY!
YEAH!
WE GOT IT!
WE FIGURED THIS [BLEEP] OUT!
DEFINITELY FIGURED IT OUT.
Carlos: I WOULD HAVE TO SAY
THAT IS A SUCCESSFUL TEST.
HELL, YEAH!
[ LINE SNAPS,
THUD ]
Fred: OH, [BLEEP]!
[BLEEP] GET
HIM OUTTA THERE.
Carlos: FRED!
Narrator: UP AHEAD...
Carlos: HOLY [BLEEP]!
GOT A NUGGET!
THEY GOT BROTHERS
AND SISTERS, RIGHT?
IT'S PROBABLY AN INDICATION
WE'RE GETTING
A LOT CLOSER
TO THAT BOTTOM.
Dustin: WE'RE HOPING THAT JUST
UNDERNEATH THAT NUGGET
IS A WHOLE BUNCH MORE.
WE FOUND GOLD, BRO!
Dustin: WOO!
Richardson: FINALLY!
WE GOT IT!
Carlos: I WOULD HAVE TO SAY
THAT IS A SUCCESSFUL TEST.
HELL, YEAH!
[ LINE SNAPS,
THUD ]
Fred: OH, [BLEEP]!
[BLEEP]
THERE'S POWER
IN THE WATER!
HOLY [BLEEP].
THAT'S SCARY
[BLEEP] MAN!
DUSTIN! KILL THE POWER!
CUT THE POWER!
Dustin: EVERYBODY OKAY?
WE GOT TO CALL IT.
THAT'S DONE.
DIVE'S DONE.
COME ON.
YOU OKAY?
YOU ALL RIGHT?
WELL, I BLEW MY ANCHORS
ON THE GRABOID.
Fred:
I HEARD.
'CAUSE I PULLED IN PROBABLY
ABOUT 8 TO 10,000 POUNDS
IN TO TIGHTEN THAT DAMN --
THE ONE ACROSS OVERHEAD.
-YEAH.
[BLEEP]
ROUGH DAY,
ROUGH DAY.
Dustin: I THOUGHT WE'D BE
PICKING UP ROCKS WAY
BIGGER THAN THAT
BEFORE IT BLEW OUT.
THAT'S PRETTY AWFUL.
Narrator: ONE OF DUSTIN'S ANCHOR
POINTS HAS FAILED.
Dustin: GOD.
SOMETHING RUBBED REAL HARD
ON THIS THING.
THAT ONE SHOWS IT
REALLY CLEARLY.
THAT'S GOT A BIG
INDENTION IN IT.
AH, LOOK.
LOOK.
THAT LITTLE BITTY EDGE
CUT THAT ROPE.
YEAH, ALL THAT JERKING
THAT WAS GOING ON
WHEN IT WAS GOING UP AND DOWN,
IT WAS JUST UP THERE DOING THIS.
JUST LIKE THIS.
AND IT CUT IT RIGHT THERE.
YUP.
SEE IT?
THAT LITTLE EDGE
JUST COST ME
A WHOLE BUNCHA MONEY
AND A LOT OF TIME.
AND IT COULDA HURT SOMEBODY.
DUSTIN, THIS MORNING,
HE'S IN TOWN
TRYING TO FIND SOME PARTS FOR
THAT ROCK LIFTER GRABOID THING
TO, UH, GET THAT THING
BACK AND OPERATIONAL.
WE JUST HAD A CRAP, UH,
LET LOOSE UP ON TOP.
UNFORTUNATELY, UH, EVERYTHING
WENT DOWN INTO THE WATER.
I HOPE THAT THING'S
GONNA DRY OUT
AND BE ALL OPERATIONAL.
I'M THINKING BRAND-NEW ANCHOR
RIGHT NOW UNLESS IT DRIES OUT.
Narrator: THE DIVE SITE IS
AT A STANDSTILL.
Dustin:
OH MY [BLEEP].
I'VE NEVER CARRIED
SO MUCH WEIGHT IN MY LIFE.
TO GET ANYMORE GOLD,
THEY HAVE TO GET
DUSTIN'S GRABOID TO WORK.
OH, MY [BLEEP].
Richardson:
WOO!
GOT THAT [BLEEP] CHAIN?
GOOD DEAL, MAN.
HOLY [BLEEP]!
THAT'S GOTTA BE
ABOUT 200 POUNDS THERE.
-[ GRUNTS ]
Dustin: YES. WHERE WERE YOU
THE WHOLE TRIP?
ALL RIGHT.
HELP ME SET IT DOWN.
AAH!
THAT WAS MY PUNISHMENT
FOR BREAKING
SOMETHING YESTERDAY.
OH, MY [BLEEP].
AHH!
I WENT ALL-OUT AND BOUGHT
THE BIGGEST DAMN CHAINS
I COULD BUY IN TOWN.
IT'S ABOUT 200 POUNDS OF CHAIN.
THEY'RE NOT COMING
LOOSE THIS TIME.
I'M NOT GIVING UP YET.
I DARE YOU TO TRY
TO BREAK THAT!
GOT BOMBER ANCHORS NOW.
YOU GONNA GO IN TODAY?
YEAH. I'LL GO IN TODAY.
ALL RIGHT.
WE JUST GOT
THE GRABOID WORKING.
AND, UH, I NEED
SOMEBODY TO GO DOWN
AND USE THIS THING
THAT CAN'T SUE ME.
I UNDERSTAND.
THERE'S A LOT
OF PINCH POINTS.
PLEASE DON'T LOSE A HAND!
JUST LOOK AT 'EM FIRST.
THEY'RE ALL THERE.
LET'S SEE IF WE GONNA HAVE 'EM
AT THE END OF THE DAY.
I MEAN, YOU CAN
MAKE A JOKE OF IT.
BUT THAT THING WILL TAKE
YOUR DAMN FINGER RIGHT OFF, MAN.
HEY, I KNOW.
HEY, LIFE IS DANGEROUS, MAN!
I MEAN, YOU KNOW,
YOU GOT, YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE AWARE OF THE DANGERS.
YOU TAKE PRECAUTIONS WITH IT.
AND, UH, DON'T PUT
STUPID PEOPLE WITH IT.
I KNOW IT'S A LITTLE BIT
OF A COMPLICATED SITUATION
WITH, UH, WORKING WITH THAT
DEVICE UNDERWATER.
IF IT CAN BE MADE
TO WORK UNDERWATER
COMFORTABLY AND SAFELY,
I CAN DO IT.
Narrator: FRED'S CAREER
AS A COMMERCIAL DIVER
MEANS HE'S HAD
THE MOST EXPERIENCE
USING HEAVY
EQUIPMENT UNDERWATER.
Dustin: HOPEFULLY.
GOTTA BE RIGHT
DOWN THERE SOMEWHERE.
WE'LL HOOK UP THE GRABOID,
PLUG THIS DAMN THING IN.
FRED'S GONNA GIVE IT A SHOT.
LITTLE WORRIED, ACTUALLY.
I -- I HOPE EVERYTHING
GOES ALL RIGHT.
I'M A LITTLE FIDGETY.
BE ON GUARD!
Carlos:
ALL RIGHT. I'M ON GUARD.
OKAY. WE'VE GOT
THE GRABOID HOOKED UP.
AND I'M COMING UP THE CABLE
WITH IT RIGHT NOW.
AND, HOPEFULLY,
THIS'LL SNATCH IT RIGHT UP.
OKAY, SO THE GRABOID
IS ALL THE WAY
UNDERNEATH THE WATER NOW.
HOW'S IT LOOKING
DOWN THERE, FRED? ALL RIGHT?
UPSTREAM,
GOING UPSTREAM.
ALL STOP.
COMING DOWN.
YEAH.
YEAH, I THINK --
WATCH OUT FOR THE BOUNCE
IF IT DOES SLIP LOOSE, FRED.
SHE WILL, UH,
JUMP IN THE AIR.
Fred: ALL RIGHT.
COMING UP.
DO WE HAVE THE ROCK?
YEAH!
WOO-HOO!
LOOK AT THAT!
HOLY [BLEEP]!
-WOO-HOO!
-IS SHE UGLY?
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
THAT'S A ROTTEN ONE!
OH, MY [BLEEP]!
LOOK AT THAT!
WOO-HOO!
HEY, TAKE A PICTURE
OF THAT RIGHT THERE.
THAT'S [BLEEP]
SWEET, DUDE!
YEAH!
WOO!
FINALLY!
CAN'T BELIEVE IT, MAN!
THE GRABOID'S DOING
ITS JOB, BROTHER!
I'D SAY THAT'S A SUCCESS.
I WOULD SAY SO.
THIS THING WORKS GREAT.
THE GRABOID'S
PICKING UP ROCKS
WE NEVER THOUGHT
IT WOULD GRAB.
LOOK AT THAT.
THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
IT GOT IT REALLY GOOD, FRED.
GOING FOR OUR LAST PUSH
BEFORE WINTER.
COULDN'T HAVE COME
AT A BETTER TIME.
FINALLY, MY RIGGING WORKS.
[ CHUCKLES ]
Carlos: YOU WANNA TAKE
YOUR MASK OFF?
Fred: OH, OKAY.
Narrator: TO MAXIMIZE DIVE TIME
AT MCKINLEY CREEK,
FRED TAKES A WORKING LUNCH.
Richardson:
WHAT DO YOU WANT, FRED?
YOU GOING TO BE ABLE TO EAT
THAT WITH THOSE GLOVES ON?
PERFECT, RIGHT THERE.
YOU GOT IT?
THERE YOU GO, FRED.
ALL RIGHT. I'M GONNA
GO GRAB ME SOME FOOD
AND BRING IT DOWN HERE.
HEY, PAUL, YOU SHOULD GO
HANG OUT WITH FRED.
OH, MAN!
WHATEVER IT TAKES.
HEY, WHAT'S UP, MAN!
[ CHUCKLES ]
BACK TO WORK, BOY!
Dustin:
THIS IS THE LAST PUSH, MAN.
WE'RE RUNNING OUTTA TIME.
THE WIND IS COMING.
LET'S GET SOME
DREDGING DONE.
Narrator:
WINTER IS ABOUT TO CALL TIME
ON THEIR SEASON.
A GIANT BOULDER HAS COST THE
DAKOTA BOYS 3 CRUCIAL DAYS
OF DREDGING.
Carlos:
THAT'S MORE LIKE IT!
BUT NOW THEY'RE BACK,
DREDGING FOR A MASSIVE DEPOSIT
OF GOLD ON BEDROCK.
WE GOT SOME GOOD DIRT COMING
OVER THE BACK OF THAT THING.
ALL RIGHT.
I AIN'T RUSHING YA, MAN.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
COME UP TODAY AT ALL.
OH, [BLEEP]. THAT LOOKS LIKE
THE GOOD STUFF RIGHT THERE.
Fred:
WHY, HELL, YEAH!
YEAH, THAT'S
WHAT IT LOOKS
LIKE COMING OVER
THE BACK OF THE BOX.
FRED, THAT LOOKS
DAMN GOOD.
THAT'S WHAT WE NEED
RIGHT THERE.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE COMING UP,
COMING UP, DIVER UP.
OH, MAN!
GOOD DAY OF DIVING!
Narrator: FRED HAS BEEN DREDGING
DEEPER THAN EVER BEFORE.
BUT NO ONE KNOWS
IF HE'S GOT DOWN
TO THE BEDROCK GOLD.
I'LL FIND OUT
HERE PRETTY SOON.
I MEAN, WE GOTTA BE
GETTING CLOSE TO THIS BEDROCK.
YOU KNOW, I NEED SOMETHING
TO COME THROUGH THAT'S, UH,
THAT SHOWS US WE'RE STILL
HEADING IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION.
HOLY [BLEEP]!
WHAT WE FINALLY
BEEN LOOKING FOR.
I GOT A NUGGET!
DAMN, THE GUYS ARE GONNA
BE HAPPY ABOUT THAT!
WE'RE FINALLY GETTING
DOWN TO SOME PAY!
THIS THING IS SO BEAUTIFUL
IT HASN'T HARDLY
TRAVELED ANYWHERE.
THAT'S ABOUT AS
ROUGH AS IT GETS.
WOO, THAT'S A NICE SELL!
I LOVE THAT SELL RIGHT THERE.
HEY, I GOT OUR LAST STUFF
OUT OF THE DREDGE
CLEANED UP AND PROCESSED.
THE GOLD IS GETTING BETTER.
[BLEEP] YEAH,
IT'S GETTING BETTER, MAN!
THAT'S GOOD GOLD, MAN!
HEY, THAT'S NICE!
Dustin:
DOESN'T PAY THE BILLS, MAN.
Richardson: AND NOW THERE'S
A NUGGET IN THERE!
NICE.
Carlos: OH,
MY [BLEEP], MAN!
Richardson:
THAT'S A BEAUTIFUL PIECE
OF GOLD RIGHT THERE.
FEW MORE OF THOSE SHOW UP,
WE GON' HAVE IT.
WELL, WHAT WE'RE
LOOKING FOR IS
A WHOLE PAN
FULLA THOSE, MAN.
THEN -- IF -- THEN, IF THAT'S
THERE, THEN YOU TELL ME.
I -- I DON'T KNOW
NOTHING ABOUT GOLD.
IF THAT'S THERE,
THEN THEY'RE --
THEY GOT BROTHERS
AND SISTERS, MAN.
WE NEED TO FIND THEIR
BIG BROTHERS NOW. AND THAT'S IT.
WE JUST GOTTA
SUCK ALL DAY, BRO.
Narrator: THE NUGGET PROVES,
BENEATH THE BIG BOULDERS,
THERE COULD BE
A LIFE-CHANGING POCKET OF GOLD.
AND NOW THEY HAVE
THE TOOLS TO REACH IT.
THAT GRABOID IS STARTING TO WORK
PRETTY DAMN GOOD RIGHT NOW.
IT'S AWESOME, MAN.
WE GONNA WONDER WHY
WE DIDN'T HAVE THAT THING
FROM THE START.
Richardson:
KEPT SAYING THAT THERE WAS
GOLD UNDERNEATH THOSE BOULDERS.
AND I THINK
YOU WERE RIGHT.!
DUDE, THIS IS WHAT WE'VE BEEN
LOOKING FOR, MAN, RIGHT?
Dustin:
THAT'S IT RIGHT THERE, MAN.
THAT'S IT.
FEEL HOW HEAVY THAT IS.
Carlos: WOW, DUDE.
THAT SOUND NEVER GETS OLD.
SURE BE NICE TO FIND
A BUNCH MORE OF THOSE!
Dustin: GOOD JOB, GUYS!
WORKING YOUR ASS OFF.
WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
I CAN FEEL IT.
THIS IS IT.
NOBODY EVER SAID
A TREASURE HUNT WAS EASY.
WE'RE HOPING THAT JUST
UNDERNEATH THAT NUGGET
THERE'S A WHOLE BUNCH MORE.
BUT IT'S JUST THE MORALE
BOOST THAT WE NEEDED.
Fred: WHEN WE GET DOWN
TO THAT BEDROCK,
I THINK THERE'S GONNA BE
A BUNCH OF GOLD
SITTING THERE WAITING
FOR YOU TO MINE 'EM.
SHIP'S SINKING,
NO FRICKING WATER,
WE WERE READY
TO FRICKING EAT EACH OTHER.
WE FOUND GOLD, BRO!
ON A SINKING SHIP,
LAND HO, MAN!
Narrator: COMING UP
ON THE SEASON FINALE...
Fred: THAT'S BEDROCK.
FINALLY!
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S MAKE SOME GOLD!
Richardson: DUDE,
CHECK THIS OUT.
Dustin: THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
WE WERE RIGHT
ON TOP OF IT.
EVERY SINGLE THING
ON HERE
HAS BEEN SPENT
ON YOUR PROJECT.
THERE'S NO MONEY LEFT.
[ RUMBLING ]
OH, MY [BLEEP]
IT'S COMING UP!
GET HIM OUTTA THERE!
HEY, FRED!
GET THE [BLEEP]
OUTTA THE WATER!
BRIDGE IS GONNA GO!
FRED!