♪♪
Dustin: ALL RIGHT.
SO, WHAT'S THE DEAL?
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
JUST STAND BY.
WE'RE WORKING ON GETTING
THE BUGS OUT OF THIS THING.
Narrator:
DEEP IN A REMOTE ALASKAN CANYON,
"GOLD RUSH" VETERANS
FRED HURT
AND HIS SON, DUSTIN --
THE DAKOTA BOYS --
ARE BACK...
LET'S DO IT.
...SEARCHING FOR GOLD.
BUT THIS TIME,
THEIR LIVES ARE ON THE LINE.
Dustin:
JUST HOLD ON TO ME.
AAH!
WHOA!
PULL. PULL. PULL.
PULL. PULL.
MAN, I LOVE YOU, MAN. COME ON.
WHY YOU GOT TO HAVE A PROBLEM?
LOOK, I DON'T WANT TO HEAR
NO MORE OF THAT [BLEEP] DUSTIN.
Man: WE'RE THE ONLY REDNECKS
CRAZY ENOUGH TO DO THIS [BLEEP]
-OH!
-DUSTIN!
Fred:
WE'RE JUST KIND OF IN THAT ZONE
BETWEEN CRAZY AND INSANE.
IF YOU'RE SCARED OF DYING,
NEVER GONNA LIVE.
OH, NO, NO, WAIT, WAIT,
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT! [BLEEP]
OH [BLEEP]
HE'S GOT NO AIR.
FRED!
NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO.
BOY, IS IT GOOD
TO GET...AIR.
OH [BLEEP]
THE BRIDGE IS GONNA GO!
GET OUT! GET OUT!
THIS IS GOLD MINING
TO THE EXTREME.
WHOO!
[ MEN SHOUT INDISTINCTLY ]
WE FOUND GOLD!
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
DISCOVERY COMMUNICATIONS
♪♪
Dustin: WHOO!
ALL WE NEED IS ONE
LITTLE POCKET OF GOLD.
THINK ABOUT IT --
ONE POCKET OF GOLD.
I WANT TO GET ENOUGH GOLD,
IT'LL JUST MOUND UP LIKE THAT.
AH, THIS IS
GONNA BE GREAT.
WE GOT EVERYTHING
PRETTY WELL SET UP.
ALL WE GOT TO DO IS WALK
INTO IT AND START MINING.
THIS IS A GENUINE
TREASURE HUNT.
Narrator: FRED HURT HAS BEEN
HUNTING FOR GOLD HERE
FOR ALMOST A DECADE,
FIRST DOWN THE VALLEY
AT PORCUPINE CREEK,
WHERE HE MINED
WITH TODD HOFFMAN.
HEY, GUYS, UH, THIS IS
A NEW MEMBER OF OUR TEAM.
UH, WELCOME ABOARD.
WHERE THE HELL
IS EVERYBODY?
Narrator:
THE NEXT YEAR...
OH!
...FRED TOOK OVER TODD'S MINE
AND BROUGHT IN
HIS GREENHORN SON, DUSTIN.
-I'M DOING GOOD.
-HUH?
HOLY [BLEEP]
[ LAUGHTER ]
SO, THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
Man: HE'S DEFINITELY GOT
THE GOLD FEVER.
WE GOT HIM HOOKED.
WHOO! WE DIGGING NOW.
Narrator: FOR 3 YEARS,
THEY MINED A MASSIVE PIT
USING CONVENTIONAL
TECHNIQUES...
THIS IS IT. THIS IS WHERE
I'M GONNA GET MY NUGGET.
...AND TOOK HOME
OVER 3/4 MILLION IN GOLD.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I THINK TONIGHT
IS A THREE-BEER NIGHT.
GOOD JOB, FRED.
[BLEEP]
Narrator: THEN, WHEN THE PIT
BECAME TOO DANGEROUS...
...FRED AND DUSTIN
HEADED UPRIVER
TOWARDS THE SOURCE
OF THE GOLD.
LET ME TELL YOU
ABOUT McKINLEY CREEK.
THERE IS A POSSIBILITY
OF BIG-TIME PAYOFF.
THEY'VE SPENT
THE LAST 2 YEARS
IN THE WILD PLUNGE POOLS
OF McKINLEY CREEK,
SEARCHING
FOR THE ULTIMATE JACKPOT,
DIVING IN WHITE WATER
WITH A SUCTION DREDGE.
NOW, THE DAKOTA BOYS RETURN
FOR A NEW SEASON
AT McKINLEY CREEK...
THERE IT IS, FRED.
HOT DAMN.
THAT IS THE CREEK,
AND IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
...ONE OF THE DEADLIEST GOLD
MINING LOCATIONS IN THE WORLD.
Fred: WHEW! LOOK AT THAT WATER
COMING OVER THAT FALLS.
IT'S KICKING BUTT.
YEAH. THAT'S A LOT
OF SNOWMELT.
IT'S SUPER DANGEROUS,
RIGHT NOW, DOWN THERE.
AND WE'RE GETTING IN IT.
ARE WE CRAZY OR WHAT?
A POCKET OF GOLD
ON THIS CREEK
COULD BE ANYWHERE
FROM 1 TO 4 MILLION BUCKS.
I THINK THAT'S GONNA
MAKE YOU A WEALTHY MAN.
AH, I CAN'T WAIT.
ALL RIGHT. LET'S DO IT.
5,000 FEET UP,
HIGH IN THE CHILKAT MOUNTAINS,
A SERIES OF GLACIERS
ERODED GOLD
FROM THE MOTHER LODE
OVER MILLIONS OF YEARS.
THEIR MELTWATER CARRIED IT
DOWN THE RUGGED CREEKS,
CREATING DEPOSITS OF GOLD
WORTH MILLIONS OF DOLLARS.
THE LOWER STRETCHES OF THE CREEK
ARE ALL BUT MINED OUT.
BUT UPSTREAM,
ON DUSTIN'S CLAIMS,
THE RAGING WHITE WATER
HAS KEPT OUT
EVEN THE TOUGHEST MINERS --
TILL THE DAKOTA BOYS
BEGAN DIVING HERE.
I BELIEVE
THAT ONE IS YOURS.
YEP.
HAVE A GOOD TRIP.
WHOO!
400 FEET OFF THE DECK.
LOOK AT THAT VIEW.
NOW, THE HARD PART STARTS.
[ LAUGHS ]
THE GRUELING JOURNEY
TO THEIR MINE SITE
IS A WALK IN THE PARK
FOR THE 39-YEAR-OLD
EXTREME SPORTS FANATIC.
Dustin:
IT'S SO HARD TO MINE HERE.
BUT IF YOU'RE SCARED OF DYING,
YOU'RE NEVER GONNA LIVE.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL GO AHEAD.
Narrator:
BUT FOR 72-YEAR-OLD FRED,
IT'S A LITTLE HARDER.
HANG ON, MAN. I GOT TO GET
MYSELF DOWN A LITTLE BIT.
SOME PEOPLE CALL ME "BIG BOOT,"
'CAUSE I GOT ONE LEG
THAT'S, UH, BENT,
TWISTED, CROOKED.
I WORKED IN REFINERIES,
CONSTRUCTION WORK.
NOTHING SLOWS ME DOWN.
HEY, I'VE BEEN MARRIED
FOR 40 YEARS.
BUT IT TOOK ME
THREE WOMEN TO DO IT.
REALLY SKETCHY SPOT.
JUST SO YOU KNOW, YOU CAN USE
THE LADDER A LITTLE BIT,
BUT IT'S ALL BANGED UP.
Fred: GET OFF THAT ROPE.
GET OUT OF THE WAY.
FRED LIKES TO THINK
HE'S IN CHARGE.
HE'S GOT HIS WAY
OF TALKING DOWN TO ME.
AND I DON'T THINK
HE MEANS IT.
BUT WHEN HE DOES IT,
IT'S ENOUGH TO SET YOU OFF.
OH, NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO, NO.
Fred: JUST WOBBLED A LITTLE BIT.
THAT'S ALL.
BUT HE'S MY DAD.
I LOVE HIM.
SO, I GOT TO
TAKE CARE OF HIM.
LET'S GO.
DON'T UNCLIP UNTIL YOU'RE GOOD
AND SAFE UP THERE, FRED.
♪♪
Dustin: NICE.
GOOD JOB, FRED.
-ALL RIGHT.
-IT'S GOOD TO BE BACK OVER HERE.
-I'M TELLING YOU.
-THIS IS WHERE WE BELONG.
Narrator: THIS TUNNEL
WAS BLASTED OUT BY OLD-TIMERS
100 YEARS AGO.
THEY BUILT A FLUME
TO DIVERT THE RAGING TORRENT,
THEN MINED THE DRIED-OUT
PLUNGE POOL
AND REAPED
OVER 4,000 OUNCES OF GOLD
WORTH OVER $5 MILLION TODAY.
OVER THE LAST 2 YEARS,
FRED AND DUSTIN
HAVE BUILT THEIR OWN MINE SITE
TO FIND GOLD
IN THE PLUNGE POOLS
JUST ABOVE THE FALLS.
Dustin: WE JUST GOT TO TURN THE
KEYS AND JUST START DREDGING.
-HOLD UP.
-HOLY [BLEEP]
UGH!
Fred: OH, MAN.
THE WATER MUST HAVE
COME UP 8 FEET.
IT'S ALL GONE, MAN --
EVERYTHING.
THERE AIN'T A THING LEFT.
NOTHING.
ALL OF OUR EQUIPMENT,
EVERYTHING THAT WAS OUT HERE,
JUST WASHED AWAY.
DREDGE,
ALL OF OUR AIR LINES.
THAT WATER JUST PUNCHED
THROUGH THERE.
IT JUST WENT
STRAIGHT OUT OF THERE.
HOLY [BLEEP]
I THINK WE HANDED IT
THE THING.
AND, UH, AND MOTHER NATURE
JUST WENT ON A RAMPAGE.
WITHOUT THIS GEAR,
WE GOT NO SEASON.
♪♪
Dustin:
DREDGE, AIR COMPRESSORS,
GENERATORS THAT --
JUST SUPER EXPENSIVE.
WELL, I JUST ABOUT PUT
JUST ABOUT ALL THE CASH
THAT I COULD EVEN THINK OF
PUTTING INTO THIS.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THE HELL WE GONNA DO.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
TO DO SOMETHING.
I MEAN, WE DON'T QUIT.
MAYBE WE CAN GET AN INVESTOR
THAT WOULD, UH,
COME ON BOARD WITH US.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW HOW TO DO
ANY OF THAT STUFF.
I CAN DIG A HOLE.
BUT I DON'T KNOW HOW TO CONVINCE
SOMEBODY TO GIVE ME MONEY.
I'M GONNA SEE
WHAT I CAN DO.
♪♪
Narrator:
TO SALVAGE HIS MINING SEASON,
FRED RESORTS TO
DESPERATE MEASURES.
WE'RE RIGHT ON THE VERGE
OF SOMETHING REALLY, REALLY BIG.
SO, I'M JUST GONNA HAVE
TO BITE THE BULLET
AND HAVE TO ASK FOR A LOAN
FROM THE LAST MAN
I WANTED TO BORROW MONEY FROM.
GOT QUITE AN OPERATION
GOING HERE.
WOW.
♪♪
I IMAGINE IT'S GONNA BE
A LITTLE BIT
OF A SURPRISE FOR HIM.
THERE HE IS,
RIGHT THERE.
HEY, UH --
HEY, TODD. OVER HERE.
Todd: LOGAN, WHO IS THAT?
IS THAT WHO I THINK IT IS?
Narrator: UP AHEAD, THE DAKOTA
BOYS REFUSE TO GIVE UP.
Dustin: COME HELL OR HIGH WATER,
THAT'S WHERE WE'RE GOING.
[BLEEP] FRED!
[BLEEP] [BLEEP]
THIS IS WHAT
WE WERE LOOKING FOR.
Fred: YEAH!
[ GROANING ]
♪♪
Narrator: TO RAISE THE MONEY HE
NEEDS TO SAVE HIS MINING SEASON,
FRED HURT HAS COME TO OLD RIVAL
TOFF HOFFMAN.
Fred: TODD HOFFMAN.
Todd: FRED HURT.
I THINK I GOT
A LITTLE PROPOSAL
YOU MIGHT POSSIBLY
BE INTERESTED IN.
COME ON OVER HERE
AND TAKE A LOOK.
YOU KNOW PORCUPINE CREEK.
-BOY, DO I.
-OH, YEAH, DO YOU.
PORCUPINE CREEK
AREA HERE,
BEEN ONE OF THE RICHEST AREAS
IN SOUTHEAST, UH, ALASKA, EVER.
ALL THEM MILLIONS
AND MILLIONS OF DOLLARS
THAT OLD MAN SCHNABEL
MINED OUT OF THERE,
IT CAME FROM
UP IN THIS AREA.
IN 1936,
THERE WAS A GLACIER
ALL UP IN THIS AREA,
RIGHT HERE.
NOW, IT HAS RECEDED
ALL THE WAY BACK UP HERE.
-YEAH.
-SO, THIS IS ALL FRESH COUNTRY.
WE GOT THESE PLUNGE POOLS
ALL ALONG McKINLEY CREEK HERE.
WE MAY GET MILLIONS.
ALL WE GOT TO DO
IS FIND THE RIGHT SPOT.
FRED, LET ME STOP YOU
RIGHT HERE.
I'VE HEARD THOSE STORIES.
I LOST $250,000
RIGHT THERE.
I NEED TO KNOW
WHY YOU'RE HERE.
I NEED AN INVESTOR.
NO KIDDING.
♪♪
I NEED ABOUT 100 GRAND.
IT'S A TREMENDOUS
AMOUNT OF MONEY.
BUT I KNOW I CAN OPERATE
AN ENTIRE YEAR,
WITH A POTENTIAL
OF A HUGE PAYBACK --
HUGE.
UM...
I DON'T THINK
YOUR CHANCES ARE THAT GOOD.
I'M GONNA BE HONEST
WITH YOU.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
THERE'S TWO GUYS THAT HAD
A DREAM ABOUT PORCUPINE.
I'VE GIVEN MINE UP.
YOU HAVEN'T.
AND MAYBE, I GAVE MINE UP
TOO EARLY.
BUT I'M
TELLING YOU WHAT --
100 GRAND'S
A LOT OF MONEY.
-ALL RIGHT.
-THE MOST I CAN DO IS $50,000.
BUT I WANT 25% OF THE GOLD
THAT YOU DIG OUT.
[ WHISTLES ]
TODD, I COULDN'T
POSSIBLY DO THAT.
DUSTIN WOULD GO BERSERK.
I WAS THINKING
MORE LIKE 10%.
OKAY, I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT I'LL DO --
AND THIS IS
MY LAST OFFER.
YOU GO 15%, AND --
AND I'LL WIRE YOU
$50,000.
YOU WANT TO TAKE IT,
OR YOU WANT TO LEAVE IT?
DUSTIN AIN'T GONNA LIKE THAT,
BUT I'M GONNA AGREE TO IT.
THANK YOU.
APPRECIATE IT.
GOOD LUCK, BIG BOOT.
YES, SIR.
I WILL BE CHECKING IN.
THIS MAY BE ONE OF THE DUMBEST
THINGS I'VE EVER DONE --
AND TRUST ME,
I'VE DONE A LOT OF DUMB THINGS.
THE 15% WAS HARD
TO SWALLOW.
BUT, UH, HEY,
WE GOT THE MONEY.
MEANS WE'RE GONNA BE
MINING THIS YEAR.
♪♪
Narrator: THE DAKOTA BOYS
HAVE JUST ENOUGH MONEY
TO REPLACE THEIR LOST
MINING EQUIPMENT.
BUT IT COMES AT A PRICE.
Dustin: COME ON, FRED.
ARE YOU JOKING?
I'M WAITING FOR YOU
TO SAY, "I'M JOKING."
I THINK YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
A HARD TIME PARTING ME
WITH THAT 15%.
RIGHT NOW,
IT'S 15% OF ZERO.
THINK OF IT THAT WAY.
IF IT'S THE ONLY THING
WE CAN DO,
AND THAT'S IT,
THEN, OKAY.
BUT THAT DON'T MEAN
I LIKE IT.
ALL RIGHT.
WHILE FRED WAS
GETTING THE LOAN,
TWO TRUSTED CREW MEMBERS
TURNED UP...
WHY, HELLO THERE.
HOW YOU DOING?
GOOD TO BE BACK UP HERE.
...FABRICATOR WES RICHARDSON
AND HIS BROTHER, PAUL,
DUSTIN'S DIVE BUDDY.
THEY'RE ON A 15%
GOLD SHARE.
I KNOW IT'S GIVING UP
WHAT'S RIGHTFULLY YOURS.
I MEAN, WE'RE UP HERE.
SO I -- WE MIGHT AS WELL STAY.
IT'D BE WAY TOO EXPENSIVE
FOR US
TO HEAD BACK HOME.
-I AGREE.
MIGHT AS WELL
STAY HERE AND GO FOR IT.
WHAT DO WE HAVE
TO LOSE NOW?
WE'RE HERE.
MY MAIN ROLE IN THIS CREW
IS, UH, I BUILD EVERYTHING.
I'VE DONE SO MUCH
WITH SO LITTLE FOR SO LONG.
I CAN DO ANYTHING
WITH NOTHING.
THIS IS MY OFFICE,
RIGHT HERE.
I LIKE TO LOOK OUT AND SEE
MOUNTAINS AND TREES, WATERFALLS.
I CAN'T DO THE CITY THING.
I'VE GOT TO BE OUT HERE IN THIS.
THIS IS ME.
THERE'S ONE OTHER THING.
JEN IS COMING.
AND ZACK IS COMING.
Narrator: ZACK SHEETS IS THE SON
OF FRED'S GIRLFRIEND, JEN.
-HOW YOU DOING?
-HEY, ZACK. I'M DUSTIN.
-NICE TO MEET YOU, DUSTIN.
-PAUL.
-HOW YOU DOING, ZACK?
I'M WES. GLAD TO MEET YOU.
-GLAD TO BE HERE.
Fred: WE NEED A GOOD,
STRONG, YOUNG MAN.
AND, UH, I THINK
YOU'LL FIT THE BILL.
Jen:
I THINK SO, TOO.
OH, YOU'RE GONNA
COME WORK WITH US.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE UP HERE
FOR A VISIT.
AND I'M HERE 'CAUSE FRED SAID
YOU GUYS NEEDED SOME HELP.
-HOW OLD ARE YOU, MAN?
-24.
HAVE YOU DONE
ANY MINING BEFORE?
NO.
YOU EVER BEEN
UNDERWATER?
NO. IT'S ALL GONNA
BE NEW FOR ME.
DAMN.
THIS IS A SUPER
DANGEROUS JOB.
AND YOU'RE SURE YOU WANT
TO GET YOURSELF INTO THIS?
'CAUSE YOU COULD
DIE OUT HERE.
YEAH. I'VE BEEN LOGGING
FOR ABOUT 8 YEARS NOW.
SO, I KNOW THAT
I'M NEW TO MINING,
BUT I'M NOT NEW
TO HARD WORK.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA GET
ANY SPECIAL TREATMENT
'CAUSE YOUR MOM'S
DATING FRED.
I DON'T WANT ANY SPECIAL
TREATMENT, DUSTIN.
I'M HERE TO WORK.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, WE'LL SEE WHAT YOU GOT,
AND, UH, WELCOME
TO THE CREW, MAN.
ALL RIGHT.
I GENERALLY TRY TO GET ALONG
WITH EVERYBODY
ON THE CREW
THAT I'M WORKING WITH.
BUT DUSTIN, HE DEFINITELY SEEMS
LIKE KIND OF A HARDASS,
AND EVEN, MAYBE,
BORDERLINE ASS[BLEEP]
BUT, UH, THAT'S OKAY,
'CAUSE I'VE WORKED WITH PEOPLE
LIKE THAT MY WHOLE LIFE.
-WE CAN USE THE HELP.
BUT NOW, I'VE GOT
A VERY, VERY YOUNG GUY.
AND I DON'T WANT THIS KID
GETTING KILLED.
♪♪
Narrator: THIS SEASON,
DUSTIN WANTS TO FIND
A NEW MINE SITE CLOSER TO
THE SOURCE OF THE GOLD.
IT'S A TREASURE HUNT.
THEY'LL SEARCH FOR A SHARP BEND
OR PLUNGE POOL
WHERE THE WATER
SLOWS DOWN
AND DEPOSITS
A MONSTER PILE OF GOLD
THAT COULD MAKE THEM
ALL RICH.
UH, WE'RE NOT GOING BACK
TO THE WATERFALL. START FRESH.
WE GOT TO GO FIND A SPOT
CLOSE TO THE SOURCE.
THE GOLD COULD BE HUGE.
BUT IT'S KIND OF
A LONG HIKE.
EVERYBODY BE SAFE.
THAT'S THE ONLY RULE.
BE SAFE. DON'T DIE.
-LET'S DO IT.
-ALL RIGHT.
Zack: OH, MY GOD.
SO, THIS IS IT, HUH?
Fred: THIS IS IT, MAN.
A LITTLE GULLIED
ACROSS THERE.
THIS IS DEFINITELY
GONNA BE MY TIME
TO, KIND OF,
BUILD THE TRUST
IN THE EQUIPMENT AND THE REST
OF THE CREW, AS WELL. SO...
SO, WHAT DO I DO FROM HERE?
-WALK OFF.
AND TRY NOT TO JUMP TOO HARD,
'CAUSE IT BOUNCES REAL HEAVY.
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
OH, NO, NO, WAIT, WAIT,
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT! WHOA.
[BLEEP]
HOLY [BLEEP]
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU [BLEEP]
[ LAUGHS ] JUST MESSING WITH HIM
A LITTLE BIT.
WHAT DID I
GET MYSELF INTO?
♪♪
-OH [BLEEP]
-WOW.
Dustin: HOW YOU DOING
BACK THERE, FRED?
I'M HANGING IN THERE.
WOW, MAN.
THERE'S SOME REALLY BIG
WATERFALLS RIGHT THERE.
THIS LOOKS GOOD, MAN.
WE HAVE TO GET DOWN.
Wes:
YEAH, WE'VE GOT TO.
JUST FIGURING OUT
HOW TO GET TO IT.
PBHT!
IT LOOKS AWFUL STEEP.
I'M GUESSING THIS IS
ABOUT 300 FEET DOWN.
I'M GONNA GO DOWN RIGHT QUICK,
AND I'LL RADIO UP TO YOU.
DON'T KNOW HOW YOU RAPPEL,
SO I DON'T WANT YOU COMING DOWN.
ALSO, YOU DON'T RAPPEL. SO,
YOU'RE NOT COMING DOWN, RIGHT?
THAT'S RIGHT.
THIS IS GOLD MINING,
UH, TO THE EXTREME.
THIS IS DANGEROUS
STUFF HERE.
WE'RE JUST KIND OF
IN THAT LITTLE ZONE
BETWEEN CRAZY AND INSANE.
ROCK!
[BLEEP] [BLEEP]
DUSTIN!
Dustin:
PLEASE DON'T KILL ME.
Narrator:
AT McKINLEY CREEK IN ALASKA...
Dustin:
PLEASE DON'T KILL ME.
...DUSTIN HURT'S SEARCH
FOR THE PERFECT PLUNGE POOL
GOLD TRAP
HAS LED HIM OVER THE EDGE
OF A CRUMBLING
250-FOOT CLIFF.
Dustin: I THINK I'M LOOKING
STRAIGHT DOWN
ON THE SPOT RIGHT NOW.
BUT THERE'S REALLY
NO GOOD WAY TO GET THERE.
THERE'S LOOSE ROCK
EVERYWHERE, MAN.
THIS IS JUST TOO DANGEROUS.
SO, LOOKS LIKE,
GOT TO GO BACK UP,
TRY TO FIND
ANOTHER WAY DOWN.
WE'VE CHOSEN A VERY HARD SPOT
TO GET TO, OBVIOUSLY.
THIS IS GONNA BE SOMETHING
REALLY HARD TO DO.
LOOKING BETTER THAN
THE OTHER SIDE.
IT'S GOT A BETTER TRAIL.
PAUL AND WES, COME ON DOWN.
AND, UH, WE COULD ALL
CHECK IT OUT TOGETHER.
-COPY THAT.
YOU'RE COMING DOWN
IN A SLIDE AREA,
SO TRY NOT TO KICK
TOO MANY ROCKS.
Zack: IT KIND OF SUCKS
BEING STUCK UP HERE
WHILE THE REST OF THE CREW'S
DOWN THERE EXPLORING
AND GETTING TO SEE
ALL THE BEAUTIFUL SCENERY.
BUT I'M LEFT UP HERE
TO WATCH FRED.
I'M BABYSITTING HIM.
NO. WE ALL KNOW
WHO'S BABYSITTING WHO HERE.
KEEP GOING.
I GOTCHA.
♪♪
I THINK THAT FLAT WE'RE LOOKING
TO BE ON IS RIGHT THERE.
Dustin: SO CLOSE, MAN.
WE CAN SEE IT.
AND IT LOOKS LIKE
I'M GONNA BE ABLE TO MAKE IT.
THERE IT IS,
RIGHT THERE, GUYS.
THIS IS WHAT
WE WERE LOOKING FOR.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
IT'S A PLUNGE POOL.
-YEAH!
-HOLY [BLEEP]
THIS IS BEAUTIFUL.
THERE'S ALL THEM ROUND BOULDERS.
I HOPE THERE'S A LOT
OF GOLD DOWN THERE -- A LOT.
HEY, FRED,
YOU GOT A COPY?
IT'S ON THE INSIDE
OF A BEND.
IT'S GOT A PLUNGE POOL AND BIG,
ROUND ROCKS THAT ARE ON A BAR.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
-YAHOO!
I THINK WE'RE GONNA DO
SOME GOOD THERE, BOY.
IT'S THE TRIFECTA.
THE TRIFECTA
OF GOLD MINING.
Narrator: THE BOULDERS,
THE BEND, AND THE PLUNGE POOL
ALL SLOW THE WATER DOWN
AND SHOULD CREATE
THE PERFECT GOLD CATCH.
WE FOUND OUR SPOT.
WE FOUND IT.
THIS IS WHAT
WE'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR,
AND IT'S BETTER
THAN WE EVER IMAGINED.
NOW THAT WE KNOW
IT'S HERE,
THERE'S NOTHING
THAT COULD STOP US -- NOTHING.
THE DAKOTA BOYS HAVE ACHIEVED
THEIR FIRST OBJECTIVE --
THE PERFECT DIVE SITE.
NEXT, THEY NEED TO BRING IN
THEIR NEW EQUIPMENT.
Dustin: IF WE CAN'T FIND
A GOOD WAY INTO THE SPOT,
I DON'T KNOW
HOW TO MINE IT.
GETTING HEAVY GEAR IN BY ROPE
IS NOT AN OPTION.
IT'S SUPER DANGEROUS.
SO, THIS IS HOW WE'RE DOING IT.
PAUL AND I,
WE'RE GONNA START
BUILDING A WALKWAY
SUSPENDED ON A CLIFFSIDE.
WE'VE GOT A LONG DAY
AHEAD OF US. OKAY?
-YEP.
-ALL RIGHT.
-OKAY.
-LET'S GO.
ACCESS TO THE TRIFECTA
IS CUT OFF
BY A 30-FOOT WALL OF ROCK.
TO GET THERE,
DUSTIN HAS TO BOLT
STEEL BRACKETS INTO THE WALL
AND ATTACH WOODEN BOARDS
TO MAKE A WALKWAY.
I'M GONNA GET YOU
TO HOLD ME OFF ON A ROPE
TO MAKE SURE,
IF I GO IN THE WATER,
YOU CAN STILL GRAB ME UP
AND GET ME OVER TO THE SIDE.
IF YOU SLIP INTO THIS WATER,
IT GETS REAL BAD.
AND YOU'RE GONNA DIE.
-COPY?
-YEP.
ANOTHER DAY
AT THE OFFICE.
WHOO-HOO!
THIS IS GONNA BE EASY.
♪♪
DONE! LET'S GET A BOARD
ON THIS THING,
GET TO THE NEXT ONE.
I THINK I'M ABOUT
HALFWAY RIGHT NOW.
AND I CAN ALMOST
TASTE IT.
[BLEEP]
DON'T STEP ON THAT.
THERE'S SOME SOFT-ASS
ROCK OVER HERE.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THE [BLEEP] TO DO.
[BLEEP] GOT ME ON EDGE.
LOOK AT THIS.
YEAH.
[BLEEP]
Narrator:
THE WALL IS MADE OF SHALE,
ONE OF ALASKA'S
SOFTEST ROCKS.
I'M STARTING TO WONDER
ABOUT THIS [BLEEP]
I DON'T KNOW
WHERE THE [BLEEP] TO GO.
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT --
THIS IS A VERY INEFFICIENT WAY
OF GETTING THINGS UP THERE.
WE GOT A LOT OF MONEY
TO PAY BACK.
AND WE AIN'T EVEN STARTED
OUR DIVING YET.
WE WON'T GET
ANYTHING DONE.
Dustin: AH [BLEEP]
THIS IS A [BLEEP] MESS.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
CALL IT QUITS.
IT SUCKS. I GOT TO FINISH
THIS WALKWAY TOMORROW.
♪♪
Narrator: THAT EVENING,
DOWN AT THE ROAD ACCESS POINT,
FRED HAS A PLAN
TO SPEED THINGS UP.
LOOK, WE NEED TO HAVE
A DISCUSSION.
WE HAVE
ALL THIS NEW STUFF.
THERE'S NEW DREDGE,
NEW HOT WATER HEATER THINGS.
THERE IS NO WAY
WE'RE GONNA GET ALL THIS STUFF
UP THAT WALKWAY
OVER THERE.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
I'VE GOT A PLAN.
I'VE CALLED UP, UH,
OUR HELICOPTER PEOPLE.
AND THEY AGREED
TO LET US PIGGYBACK
ON A JOB GOING ON
IN THIS AREA OVER HERE,
SAVING $7,000
RIGHT OFF THE BAT.
ALL RIGHT.
SO, WHAT DAY IS THAT?
THAT IS TOMORROW.
PROBABLY 10:00.
-PROBABLY.
-IT'S TOO CLOSE.
WE'RE NOT PREPARED
FOR IT.
WE HAVE TO SET UP AN AREA
TO LAND ALL THIS STUFF.
PLANS CHANGE
ALL THE TIME.
THERE'S ABSOLUTELY,
WE HAVE TO HAVE IT.
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
ALL RIGHT [BLEEP] IT.
SOUNDS LIKE WE GOT A PLAN.
LET'S GET TO THAT,
SEE WHAT WE CAN DO.
-OKAY.
Narrator:
COMING UP IN THIS SERIES...
Dustin: OH [BLEEP]
-BRIDGE IS GONNA GO!
-GET OUT! GET OUT!
OHH!
-PULL. PULL.
-[ GROANING ]
Dustin: I'LL BE DAMNED.
WE FOUND NUGGETS.
YEAH! WHOO-HOO-HOO!
WE FOUND GOLD!
Narrator:
AT PORCUPINE CREEK,
FRED HAS TWO HOURS
TO BOX UP HIS MINING EQUIPMENT
TO HELI-LIFT IT UP
TO THE MINE SITE.
THESE HELICOPTER LIFTS
ARE NOTHING I TAKE LIGHTLY
BECAUSE THEY'RE JUST
SO DAMNED EXPENSIVE.
I MEAN, THIS LIFT IS
RUNNING $2,500 AN HOUR.
LOOK. EVERY SECOND'S
GONNA COUNT HERE.
Narrator: TWO MILES
UP AT McKINLEY CREEK...
...DUSTIN HAS
A MUCH TOUGHER JOB --
GET TO THE ONE
PIECE OF FLAT LAND
BY THE TRIFECTA POOL
AND CLEAR THE TREES
TO CREATE THE DROP ZONE.
I NEED TO PUT SOME
GOOD ANCHOR BOLTS.
AND THIS STUFF GETS SOFT
AND GONNA BREAK OFF.
I DON'T HAVE ANY CHOICE.
Narrator:
DUSTIN WEIGHS OVER 200 POUNDS.
TO PROGRESS,
HE MUST TRUST HIS LIFE
TO A SINGLE UNTESTED
ANCHOR POINT.
IT BREAKS, I'M GOING SWIMMING.
WHOO-HOO!
THAT'S WHAT GOOD, SOLID
ROCK FEELS LIKE, RIGHT THERE.
Narrator:
FINALLY ON THE FLAT GROUND...
Dustin: YEAH!
...THEY HAVE LESS
THAN 20 MINUTES
TO CREATE A LANDING ZONE.
[ HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING ]
THERE'S -- HE'S COMING.
PAY ATTENTION.
YOU'LL SEE THIS GOES QUICK,
QUICK, QUICK, QUICK,
LIKE BAM, BAM, BAM, BAM, BAM.
GOOD?
GET BACK!
HE'S COOKING, MAN.
PORCUPINE TO DUSTIN.
WHAT'S UP, FRED?
HOPE YOU GOT
THAT THING READY.
WE GOT THE HELICOPTER
IN THE AIR.
COPY THAT. KEEP CUTTING.
I'LL CLEAN UP.
THERE IT IS RIGHT NOW.
[BLEEP]
WE AIN'T GOT THE SPOT YET.
GOOD ENOUGH.
IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
PERFECT.
ONE DOWN.
-THAT WAS CLOSE.
-YEP.
Narrator:
IN JUST OVER AN HOUR,
DUSTIN LANDS
5 TONS OF EQUIPMENT,
FUEL, AND LUMBER,
KEEPING THE HELICOPTER
COST TO $3,000.
WE'RE ESTABLISHING
A HOME BASE.
THIS IS GOOD, MAN.
-YEP.
-HEY, GOOD JOB, FELLAS.
GOOD JOB SENDING
ALL THAT STUFF UP, FRED.
YOU DIDN'T LOSE
ANYTHING AT ALL.
I'M PROUD OF YOU, MAN.
HEY, "A"-PLUS, MAN.
WE ALWAYS DO IT.
[ LAUGHS ]
[ RADIO BEEPS ]
Narrator: 10 DAYS AFTER
ARRIVING IN ALASKA,
THE DAKOTA BOYS CAN HIKE IN
AND SET UP FOR THEIR FIRST
DIVE OF THE SEASON.
Fred:
I'M HOPING IT'S GONNA GO WELL.
AND WE'RE GONNA FIND OUT
IF, UH, WE GET DOWN THERE
AND GET GOOD RESULTS.
Dustin:
GONNA BE A GREAT DAY TODAY.
WE GOT TO GO FIND
SOME SORT OF GOLD
TO MAKE THIS ALL WORTH IT.
IT'S A BIG DEAL.
COME HELL OR HIGH WATER,
THAT'S WHERE WE'RE GOING.
I'LL TAKE SOME SAMPLES.
HOPEFULLY, IT'LL GIVE US
AN INDICATION
OF WHAT'S TO COME IN THIS AREA.
♪♪
Narrator:
FRED HAS 10 YEARS EXPERIENCE
DIVING IN THE GULF OF MEXICO.
ALL RIGHT. SO YOU KNOW
WHERE THAT'S GOING, RIGHT?
-NO.
-SO, AN AIR LINE GOES IN THAT.
Narrator:
DUSTIN IS A SELF-TAUGHT EXPERT
AT DIVING IN WHITE WATER.
SO WE'RE GONNA SET UP
AN AIR LINE.
ALL RIGHT.
I NEED TO GO
AND GET MY [BLEEP] DONE FIRST.
PUT A WET SUIT ON.
WE'LL BE MAKING
SOME ADJUSTMENTS.
I GUARANTEE.
WE CAN DO ALL THAT STUFF
ONCE I GET SUITED UP.
EVERY SECOND,
AROUND 2,000 GALLONS
OF FREEZING WATER SURGE
THROUGH THIS PLUNGE POOL.
TO KEEP HIM ALIVE,
DUSTIN NEEDS SPECIALLY
ADAPTED DIVE EQUIPMENT.
Dustin: WHAT I NEED NOW IS MY
BODY HARNESS, THEN LEADS.
-AND THIS IS LIKE A FITTING.
-YEP.
Narrator: HE'LL BE CONNECTED
TO THE DIVE STATION
BY AN UMBILICAL LIFELINE
MADE UP OF THREE
CRUCIAL COMPONENTS.
TO STOP HIM BEING SWEPT AWAY,
HE'S ATTACHED
TO A PARACORD SAFETY ROPE
WITH A BREAKING STRAIN
OF 2,000 POUNDS.
A HOSE PUMPS HOT WATER
AROUND THE SUIT
TO PREVENT HYPOTHERMIA.
THE SECOND HOSE
DELIVERS VITAL AIR.
A FAULT WITH ANY OF THESE
WOULD BE LIFE-THREATENING.
LET'S GO AHEAD
AND MOVE THIS.
GIVE IT A LITTLE
EXTRA SLACK.
RIGHT.
Dustin: IF YOU GET IN THE DAMN
WATER, AND YOU GET TANGLED UP
IN YOUR CABLES AND ROPES
AND ALL THIS OTHER JUNK,
WE'RE GONNA DIE.
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S GOOD.
VERY GOOD.
EXCELLENT.
MIGHT WANT TO GET
A LITTLE BIT TIGHTER, MAN.
A LITTLE BIT TIGHTER ON TOP.
JUST TAKE YOUR TIME.
JUST 'CAUSE WE GOT
A CAMERA ON US
DON'T MEAN WE GOT TO
HURRY THE [BLEEP] UP.
YOU KNOW, ESSENTIALLY,
I'VE GOT HIS LIFE IN MY HANDS.
OH, I DEFINITELY GET NERVOUS.
ANYTHING GOES WRONG, WE'RE OUT
IN THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE.
THAT WOULD BE THE END OF HIM.
Dustin: ALL RIGHT. SO WHAT'S
THE -- WHAT'S THE DEAL?
HOOK UP YOUR, UH,
LINE RIGHT HERE.
THE AIR HOSE IS
A LITTLE CRAZY, I THINK.
THERE AIN'T NOTHING
WRONG WITH IT.
LOOK AT THIS.
DO YOU SEE HOW STUPID THIS IS?
IT'S AN AIR HOSE,
AND IT'S IN RAPIDS.
THIS ISN'T REGULAR WATER.
IT'S GONNA WRAP AROUND YOUR ARM.
IT'S GONNA --
IT JUST -- IT JUST SUCKS.
THERE IS NOTHING
WRONG WITH IT.
I SAID, "I'M GOING
TO PUT ON MY SUIT.
-DON'T DO --"
-I TOLD YOU TO STAND BY...
"DON'T DO THIS."
...UNTIL WE GOT THIS THING DONE.
"I'LL COME BACK."
I COME BACK, IT -- IT'S DONE.
WHO DID IT?
YOU DID IT? WAS IT YOU?
DID YOU GUYS
TAPE THIS THING TOGETHER?
NO? SO IT WAS OBVIOUSLY YOU.
AND NOW IT'S WRONG.
LOOK, I DON'T WANT TO HEAR
NO MORE OF THAT [BLEEP] DUSTIN.
[BLEEP] WE COULD DO THIS
WITHOUT YOU IF YOU WANT.
SOMEBODY CUT ALL
THE [BLEEP] LOOSE, PLEASE.
Y'ALL DON'T NEED ME.
Y'ALL ALL [BLEEP]
EXPERIENCED.
YOU CAN DO IT YOURSELF.
I IMAGINE ANYBODY
WOULD BE VERY UPSET
WITH HAVING SOMEONE
TALK TO YOU LIKE THAT,
PARTICULARLY
A-A FATHER AND SON.
THIS IS MY PLACE.
HIS JOB IS TO HELP ME,
NOT THE OTHER WAY AROUND.
Narrator: UP AHEAD...
GOT A LITTLE SAMPLE
FOR YOU GUYS.
Paul: BRING IT UP.
BRING IT UP. BRING IT UP.
SOME LITTLE FLASHES.
HEY! COME HERE.
CHECK IT OUT, FELLAS!
Narrator:
AT McKINLEY CREEK,
DUSTIN'S FIRST DIVE
FOR GOLD IS ON HOLD.
YOU KEEP, LIKE, TREATING ME
LIKE A KID
LIKE I'VE NEVER
DONE THIS BEFORE.
I HAVE MORE EXPERIENCE
IN IT THAN YOU DO.
IN THIS? YOU DON'T.
IF WE CAN WORK TOGETHER,
IT'LL BE GREAT.
YOU'RE MY FATHER.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE MY BOSS.
WHY DON'T YOU
COME BE PART OF THIS?
PUT THE DAMN MASK ON
AND GET IN THE WATER
AND DO YOUR DAMN JOB.
Narrator: IN ALASKA,
DUSTIN HURT IS READY
TO RISK HIS LIFE
DIVING IN ICE COLD WHITEWATER.
A SAMPLE FROM THE CREEK BED
COULD INDICATE
A GOLD DEPOSIT
WORTH MILLIONS OF DOLLARS.
FRED AND I FIGHT.
WE'LL MAKE UP LATER.
BUT RIGHT NOW,
WE NEED TO GET THIS HOLE
AND GET A SAMPLE OUT.
LET'S [BLEEP] DO THIS ANYWAY.
COME ON.
LET'S HOOK ME UP.
Narrator: DUSTIN MUST DIVE
THROUGH A CURRENT
POWERFUL ENOUGH
TO MOVE HALF-TON BOULDERS.
Dustin: ALL RIGHT.
Paul: GOOD LUCK!
[ DUSTIN GROANS ]
OH [BLEEP]
WHOA!
AAH!
[ GROANING ]
THAT'S CRAZY.
PULL. PULL. PULL.
PULL. PULL.
TAKE HIM THAT WAY.
[ DUSTIN GROANING ]
MAN.
THAT WATER IS
SERIOUSLY RAGING NOW.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO DO
SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
IF WE START DOWN THERE
AND WORK OUR WAY IN,
IT WON'T BE THIS VIOLENT.
-YEAH, I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
Narrator: THE NEW PLAN --
START IN A CALM AREA
FURTHER DOWNSTREAM.
THEN WORK BACK UP
TO THE PLUNGE POOL.
[ DUSTIN GROANS ]
COME ON.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
WHAT WAS THAT AGAIN?
[ GROANS ]
WATCH OUT.
AAH. [BLEEP]
WHOA.
THAT'S JUST GONNA PULL ME IN.
-DUSTIN.
-DO YOU GOT A COPY?
-UH-OH.
-OH [BLEEP]
OH, GOOD GOD.
DUSTIN?
PULL. PULL.
-WHOO!
-[ LAUGHS ]
THAT WAS FUN!
YEE-HAW!
[ LAUGHS ]
GOT MATERIAL?
GOT A LITTLE SAMPLE
FOR YOU GUYS.
ALL RIGHT.
OH [BLEEP]
HEAVY.
WELL, LET'S SEE
IF IT PANS OUT.
ALL RIGHT.
I COULDN'T STAY
ON THE BOTTOM FOR VERY LONG,
BUT THE STUFF I COULD GRAB,
IT LOOKED PRETTY GOOD.
IT LOOKED LIKE THE STUFF
I'M LOOKING FOR DOWN THERE.
-HEY, CHECK IT OUT.
-SO HOW'D IT GO?
WE WENT AND FOUND
A LITTLE BIT OF SURFACE DIRT.
DO YOU MIND, UH,
PANNING UP SOME OF THAT?
-YEAH, WE CAN TRY.
-YEP.
THANK YOU, FRED.
Narrator:
ANY GOLD WILL LIKELY BE BURIED
TOO DEEP IN THE CREEK BED
FOR DUSTIN'S
SMALL TEST SAMPLE.
IT'S PRETTY HEAVY STUFF.
YOU CAN'T GET GOLD
RIGHT OFF THE SURFACE.
Narrator: INSTEAD, FRED HOPES
TO FIND OTHER HEAVY MINERALS,
TELLTALE SIGNS OF A GOLD POCKET.
♪♪
HOW'S IT LOOKING, FRED?
WELL, SO FAR,
I DON'T SEE TOO MUCH
PROMISING STUFF THERE.
I DON'T KNOW IF I WAS DIGGING
IN THE RIGHT SPOTS.
I WAS TRYING MY HARDEST
TO STAY DOWN.
TELL YOU WHAT.
SEE SOME LITTLE FLASHES.
BUT I THINK IT'S PYRITE.
-A LOT OF PYRITE IN THAT THING.
-A-HA.
Narrator: IRON PYRITE,
ALSO KNOWN AS FOOL'S GOLD,
IS DENSE AND VERY OFTEN COLLECTS
IN THE SAME PLACE AS REAL GOLD.
PYRITE IS WORTHLESS.
BUT IT'S A GOOD
INDICATOR OF GOLD.
LITTLE BITTY STUFF,
BUT IT'S THERE.
IT'S LOOKING GOOD.
HEY! COME HERE.
CHECK IT OUT, FELLAS!
-ALL THAT STUFF.
-OH, YEAH.
WHAT THE HELL
IS UNDERNEATH ALL OF THAT?
LET'S SEE
WHAT'S DOWN THERE.
-WHOO!
-GOOD JOB, DUSTIN.
GOOD JOB, GUYS.
-YEAH.
BEEN WORKING WITH THESE GUYS
FOR THREE YEARS NOW.
AND I THINK FINALLY THIS YEAR,
WE'RE THERE WHERE
WE NEED TO BE.
Fred:
WE HAVE A WHOLE BUNCH OF PYRITE.
MAN, IT CHANGED EVERYTHING.
THAT WAS OUR SAVIOR
POINT RIGHT THERE.
I KNOW THIS IS GONNA BE
A GREAT SEASON.
I KNOW WHERE THE GOLD IS.
AND IT'S RIGHT THERE
SAYING, "HEY, I'M DOWN HERE!
HELP! I NEED TO BE
IN YOUR POCKET!"
[ LAUGHING ]
Narrator:
COMING UP THIS SEASON...
WELL, WE DON'T HAVE ANY GOLD
FOR YOU RIGHT NOW.
HEY. WHAT DID I PUT
IN 50 GRAND FOR, THIS TENT?
-YOU MUST BE CARLOS.
-YES, SIR.
TODD HOFFMAN SENT HIM UP HERE
TO KEEP AN EYE ON US.
THESE GUYS CAN THROW ME
IN THE CREEK.
PULL IT OUT OF THE WATER!
YEAH!
-OH [BLEEP]
-FRED!
NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO.
Dustin: I'LL BE DAMNED.
WE FOUND NUGGETS.
-YEAH!
-WHOO-HOO-HOO!
WE FOUND GOLD!
WHEN I'M DONE WITH THIS,
I WANT TO BE A MILLIONAIRE.
OH [BLEEP]
BRIDGE IS GONNA GO!
GET OUT! GET OUT!
THIS IS HOW IT IS MINING
IN ALASKA, MAN.
ONE MINUTE,
YOU THINK YOU GOT IT.
NEXT MINUTE,
EVERYTHING'S GONE.