I WAS DIVING,
AND THE WHOLE CREEK WENT BLACK.
SO WE KIND OF FEEL LIKE
THERE'S SOMETHING
HAPPENING UPCREEK
FROM US RIGHT NOW.
AND I DON'T KNOW
HOW DANGEROUS IT IS.
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT
UP THERE?
HOLY COW.
OH.
LANDSLIDE.
IT'S COMPLETELY
ACROSS THE CREEK.
IF THE TOPSIDE OF THAT
THING BLOCKS OFF,
IT'LL CREATE A DAM.
AND IT WILL FILL
UP BEHIND THAT.
THERE'S A POTENTIAL
WE CAN GET, UH, LIKE, UH...
A COLLAPSE HERE.
...INLAND TSUNAMI.
IT WILL KICK OUR ASS.
WOW.
Dustin: ALL RIGHT, FELLAS,
HUDDLE UP REAL QUICK.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS.
WE'RE GONNA GO UPSTREAM.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WAIT.
GO OUT AND FORMULATE
EXACTLY -- I KNOW.
YOU CAN'T STAND IT.
YOU HAVE TO LEAVE.
Dustin: FRED'S TRYING TO
MAKE A DECISION
THAT COULD COST ME WEEKS.
I DON'T HAVE A LOT
OF WEEKS RIGHT NOW.
Paul: LOOK AT THE WATER.
Dustin: WATER DROPPED 10 INCHES
IN A COUPLE MINUTES.
THAT MEANS THERE'S A WALL
OF WATER GONNA COME.
WE RUN FOR THE HILLS
AS FAST AS WE CAN.
MIGHT BE A CHANCE
TO MAKE GOLD TODAY.
HEY, THERE'S ACTUALLY
SOMETHING IN THERE
THAT LOOKS LIKE A NUGGET.
YEAH.
YOU MAY KISS YOUR BRIDE.
I'M GOING TO GET
MY GOLD THIS WEEKEND.
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
DISCOVERY COMMUNICATIONS
Dustin: FRED AND I HAVE HAD
A COMPLICATED SEASON.
I'VE GOT A GREAT CREW. THEY'VE
WORKED THEIR ASS OFF FOR ME.
BUT HAVEN'T GIVEN
THESE GUYS ANY GOLD YET.
MY FIRST DAY UP HERE,
I WAS EXCITED, FULL OF ENERGY.
NOW I'M -- I'M EXHAUSTED
IN EVERY WAY, SHAPE, AND FORM.
I'D LOVE TO HAVE GOLD
IN MY POCKET
TO MAKE IT ALL WORTH IT.
BUT I'M ON A GREAT ADVENTURE.
AND THIS IS HOW I CHOSE
TO GO ABOUT IT.
GOT TO DO SOMETHING
DIFFERENT OR ELSE
THIS WHOLE SEASON'S
GONNA BE A FAILURE.
Dustin:
CARLOS IS GOING DOWN TODAY.
HE CAME UP WITH A WAY
TO TRY TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO TAKE A LOOK
AT THE BOTTOM.
IT'S PRETTY DEEP DOWN THERE.
NOW, THESE ARE SOME SERIOUS
POWERFUL UNDERWATER LIGHTS.
AND, UH, I WANT TO GET
A VIEW OF EVERYTHING
THAT YOU COULD SEE DOWN THERE.
Narrator:
IN ALASKA, THE DAKOTA BOYS
HAVE BEEN SEARCHING
FOR A POCKET OF GOLD
WORTH MILLIONS OF DOLLARS.
ALL RIGHT.
GOING DOWN.
BUT EIGHT WEEKS INTO THE SEASON,
THEY'VE FOUND LESS
THAN $800 WORTH.
Dustin:
WE ARE WORKING WAY TOO HARD
TO NOT HAVE GOLD.
WE SHOULD HAVE -- OUR POCKETS
SHOULD BE LINED WITH THIS STUFF.
Narrator: AND THEY HAVE TO REPAY
A $50,000 LOAN
TO TODD HOFFMAN
BEFORE ANY OF THEM
GET TO SHARE A CENT.
SURE YOU WANT TO
DO A CLEAN OUT?
I DON'T THINK WE GOT
A SINGLE THING IN THERE.
A FEW SPECKS IS JUST
GONNA PISS ME OFF.
FRED AND DUSTIN ARE
UNDER PRESSURE TO DELIVER.
Dustin: NO DOUBT, I'M STARTING
TO BECOME IMPATIENT.
HEY, CARLOS.
YOU GOT DUSTIN ON THE MIC.
Carlos:
ALL RIGHT, DUSTIN.
TELL ME WHAT'S
GOING ON, MAN.
Narrator: SINCE INSTALLING
A DIVERSION,
THE CREW HAS DREDGED
AN AREA DOWNSTREAM.
BUT THEY'VE YET TO HIT BEDROCK.
HEY, MAN. DO YOU THINK
YOU CAN GET UP
AND GO CHECK OUT
THOSE BOARDS?
DUSTIN NOW WANTS TO
EXPLORE MINING UPSTREAM.
Dustin:
SEASON IS HALFWAY THROUGH,
AND WE'VE GOT NOTHING
BUT A HOLE TO SHOW FOR IT.
IF YOU CAN GET UP
INTO THAT CORNER,
IT WOULD BE AWESOME.
BUT I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU CAN OR NOT.
WELL, JUST ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THAT DIVERSION,
I THINK THERE'S GOLD
AND A LOT OF IT.
WE PROBABLY PUT THE DIVERSION
WALL IN THE WRONG SPOT.
THAT'S WHERE YOU WERE AT
WHEN YOU FOUND THAT NUGGET.
I THINK IT'S TIME
TO FIND MORE.
IT'S TIME TO FIND SOME GOLD,
MAN, STRAIGHT UPSTREAM.
Narrator:
FOUR WEEKS AGO, DUSTIN FOUND
A NUGGET BY THE PLUNGE POOL,
A SIGN THE ENTIRE BEND
COULD BE RICH IN GOLD.
THEY BUILT A DIVERSION
TO CREATE A SAFE DIVING AREA
AND HAVE EXCAVATED
A LARGE SECTION
IN THE DOWNSTREAM END.
NOW, HAVING FOUND LESS
THAN AN OUNCE OF GOLD,
DUSTIN WANTS TO MOVE
BACK UPSTREAM,
TUNNEL DOWN TO WHERE HE BELIEVES
THE GOLD IS CONCENTRATED
DIRECTLY BENEATH THE NUGGET.
Dustin:
I'M SICK OF NOT SEEING GOLD.
I'M ACTUALLY HEAVING
STRESS ABOUT IT.
I CAN'T SLEEP AT NIGHT.
WE'RE GONNA GO UPSTREAM.
I'VE SEEN GOLD THERE.
I NEED TO FIND OUT
WHAT'S IN THERE.
IT'S MORE IMPORTANT TO ME
THAN ANY OTHER THING
OUT HERE RIGHT NOW.
I NEED THAT TO HAPPEN.
Fred: WELL, I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT, UH THAT.
YOU WANT TO GO INTO
THE DIVERSION AND GO UPSTREAM?
FINE.
BUT LET'S FIND OUT
WHAT'S DOWNSTREAM FIRST.
Dustin: THERE WILL BE NO GOLD
IN THERE AT ALL.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WAIT.
LET ME FINISH ONE SENTENCE.
GO OUT AND FORMULATE
EXACTLY -- I KNOW.
YOU CAN'T STAND IT.
YOU HAVE TO LEAVE.
THIS IS TYPICAL.
Fred: THEY NEED TO CUT OFF
ALL THAT [BLEEP]
GOING UP INTO THE
BEHIND THE DIVERSION.
WE'VE GOT A NICE HOLE
10-OR-12-FEET WIDE.
THEY JUST NEED TO
KEEP GOING DOWNSTREAM.
Narrator:
FRED AND DUSTIN ARE PARTNERS.
BUT DUSTIN OWNS THIS CLAIM.
Dustin: FRED'S TRYING TO TAKE
CONTROL OF THE SITUATION.
BUT I DON'T LIKE IT,
NOT ONE BIT.
FRED'S TRYING TO MAKE DECISIONS
THAT COULD COST ME WEEKS
IF HE'S WRONG -- WEEKS.
I DON'T HAVE A LOT OF WEEKS
RIGHT NOW.
I THINK THERE'S GOLD AND A LOT
OF IT STRAIGHT UPSTREAM.
IT'S NOT STREAM.
Narrator:
DUSTIN GOES AHEAD REGARDLESS.
GONNA DO
THE UN-SMART THING.
AND I'M GOING STRAIGHT DOWN,
BASICALLY A TUNNEL.
MIGHT BE A LITTLE UNSAFE.
TO EXCAVATE DOWN
THROUGH THE BOULDERS
AND BENEATH THE DIVERSION,
DUSTIN RISKS SERIOUS INJURY
FROM UNSTABLE ROCKS.
[ GROANS ]
THAT WAS STUPID.
YOU READY?
ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE COMING UP.
HERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT.
WOW.
THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
DUSTIN.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
UH...
Dustin:
ROCKSLIDES UNDERWATER ARE SLOWER
BUT STILL TERRIFYING.
AND IT'S ALL BECAUSE
I WENT WITH THE UNSAFE
PLAN BY DIGGING
STRAIGHT DOWN.
IT'S MY OWN DAMN FAULT
IF I GET HURT.
Fred: WELL, WE DIDN'T DO
A WHOLE LOT TODAY.
UH, NOTHING
BUT MOVING ROCKS.
WE NEED TO BE DREDGING
WHERE THE HOLE IS.
WE'RE LOOKING
IN THE WRONG PLACE.
Dustin:
THIS IS A MINOR [BLEEP] SETBACK.
THAT'S IT.
Narrator: UP AHEAD...
Dustin: HOLY COW.
[ LAUGHS ]
LANDSLIDE.
IT WILL KICK OUR ASS.
I'M GOING TO GET
MY GOLD THIS WEEKEND.
YOU MAY KISS YOUR BRIDE.
♪♪
Fred: WE HAVEN'T BEEN
FINDING ANY GOLD.
DEBATE IS TO WHERE
THE DAMN GOLD IS.
TODAY, I'M GONNA GET IN THERE
AND DO MY OWN THING.
I KNOW DUSTIN.
HE'S UNDER STRESS WANTING
TO GO BUSTING INTO
THAT DAM UPSTREAM
WHERE WE FOUND ONE NUGGET.
IT'S NOT THE WAY TO GO.
[BLEEP] THIS.
Narrator: TODAY, IT'S "DAKOTA"
FRED'S TURN TO DIVE.
INSTEAD OF CONTINUING
DUSTINGS UPSTREAM TUNNEL,
FRED'S GOING BACK
TO THE ORIGINAL PLAN,
EXPANDING THE WIDE AREA
IN THE DOWNSTREAM SECTION
OF THEIR DIVE POOL.
I APPROACH THINGS MORE LOGICAL.
I WANT TO ELIMINATE
THE FIRST POSSIBILITY
OF THE GOLD BEING DOWNSTREAM.
SOMETIMES, IT TAKES
A LITTLE MORE EXPLAINING
TO GET IT THROUGH
SOME THICK SKULLS
AS TO WHAT'S GOING ON.
FIRE IT UP.
OOH-HOO-HOO.
WOW.
Narrator:
DOWNSTREAM, THEY'VE ALREADY
MOVED THE WORST OF THE BOULDERS.
AND 10 FEET
BENEATH THE SURFACE,
FRED CAN GET STRAIGHT
INTO DREDGING FOR GOLD.
Fred: LET ME WARM
THIS SUIT UP.
HEY. I'M GONNA SHOW YOU
FELLAS HOW IT'S DONE.
UH, WE GOT FRED DOWN.
HE SEEMS TO BE
DIGGING IT RIGHT.
HE'S DIGGING COMPLETE
OPPOSITE WAY OF EVERYONE ELSE.
FRED DECIDED, UH,
HE KNOWS BETTER.
SO HE'S DIGGING THAT DIRECTION,
I THINK, DOWNCREEK.
OH, I CAN'T WAIT TO SIT DOWN
AND LOOK IN THAT BOX,
SEE WHAT'S IN THERE.
Narrator:
SUBMERGED IN THE 38-DEGREE
WATER FOR FOUR HOURS,
FRED HAS RUN NEARLY SIX YARDS
OF MATERIAL THROUGH THE DREDGE.
COPY THAT.
YOU'RE COMING UP.
THAT WAS A LONG
DIVE TODAY, FRED.
I THINK WE NAILED THAT ONE.
HIT THE POWER.
LET'S SEE WHAT
WE GOT IN THE BOX.
I DON'T SEE ANY GOLD.
[BLEEP].
NOTHING.
THAT'S NOT WHAT
I WANTED TO SEE.
NO.
LET'S LOOK UP AT THE TOP.
WHAT YOU GOT?
NO GOLD. NO GOLD.
NO GOLD.
I DON'T SEE ANY NUGGETS.
WHICH WE MAY NOT...
WE'RE STILL NOT
IN THE RIGHT SPOT.
I THINK WE NEED
TO BE FURTHER UPSTREAM.
I GUESS IT'S SLOWER
GOING THAN I THOUGHT.
OH, WELL.
Dustin: FRED AND I ARGUED
AND BITCHED ABOUT WHAT TO DO.
AND HE JUST COULDN'T
LISTEN, MAN.
IT'S RIDICULOUS.
I'VE WASTED A LOT
OF TIME ON THIS.
I WON'T BE WASTING
ANY MORE TIME.
I CAME UP WITH A PLAN.
AND WE'RE STICKING TO IT.
Narrator:
THE CREW HAS NOTHING TO SHOW
FOR A DAY'S DIVING.
ALL MINING FROM NOW
ON WILL FOCUS UPSTREAM.
HOLY [BLEEP].
NOT SURE WHAT'S GOING ON.
LAST FEW TIMES IT RAINED,
IT DIDN'T DO THIS.
LOOKS PRETTY BAD.
I GUESS THAT RAIN DID A LOT.
Narrator: OVERNIGHT, HEAVY RAIN
IN THE MOUNTAINS
HAS RAISED THE LEVEL
OF THE CREEK BY THREE FEET.
Carlos: LOOK HOW FAST THAT
WATER'S MOVING, MAN.
THAT'S FAST-MOVING
WATER RIGHT THERE.
IT'S JUST THIS [BLEEP]
DANG CREEK
DON'T WANT US HERE, MAN.
AND TODAY, IT'S CARLOS'
TURN TO DIVE.
MY MAIN CONCERN IS THAT
[BLEEP] DANG DIVERSION WALL.
IF IT BREAKS, IT'S GONNA
CAUSE A LOT OF PAIN,
BRO, A LOT OF PAIN.
THIS IS A LITTLE BIT
BEAUCOUP UNNERVING, BROTHER.
Dustin:
STUFF'S ANGRY, AIN'T IT?
THAT'S VERY,
VERY ANGRY, MAN.
HOW YOU FEELING ABOUT THAT?
I'M JUST WONDERING,
WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT THAT DIVERSION
HOLDING THROUGH?
IT'S A HIGH-RISK
SITUATION RIGHT NOW.
CARLOS, I'M NOT SURE
HOW COMFORTABLE I AM
WITH YOU GOING
DOWN THERE TODAY.
WE MAY...
I -- I'M NOT SURE
HOW COMFORTABLE I AM
WITH ANYBODY PUTTING THAT --
PUTTING THAT DREDGE IN,
DUDE.
I WON'T PUT YOU
IN A SITUATION
THAT I WOULDN'T
PUT MYSELF IN.
I CAN DIG IN THAT.
Narrator: WATER IS NOW CRASHING
DOWN THE CREEK
AT OVER 8,000 GALLONS A SECOND.
Dustin: IT'S DANGEROUS.
BUT I DON'T KNOW FOR ME
TO BE WEIRDED OUT BY IT.
Narrator:
DUSTIN'S DETERMINED TO CONTINUE
TUNNELING BENEATH THE DIVERSION.
Dustin: GOT TO GET IN
THE MIND SET
EVERY HOUR COUNTS,
EVERY ROCK COUNTS.
I MEAN, IT DOESN'T STOP.
OH.
HOLY MOLY.
THIS THING'S STRONG, DUDE.
YEAH.
[BLEEP]
IT'S STRONG RIGHT NOW.
CURRENT IS VERY,
VERY STRONG.
YOU FALL IN THIS THING
RIGHT HERE, JUST FALL DOWN.
WE'RE READY TO GO.
JUST BE CAREFUL DOWN THERE.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT THE BOULDER
SITUATION'S LIKE NOW.
HEY, DUSTIN!
WHAT?
WHOA.
Carlos:
WATER'S GETTING DIRTIER.
THE WATER'S GETTING DIRTIER.
I KNOW.
YEAH.
IT'S GETTING DARKER
BY THE MINUTE.
YEAH.
Dustin: IT'S NOW GOT REALLY,
REALLY DIRTY HERE.
♪♪
Narrator:
IN MCKINLEY CREEK, THE WATER
HAS SUDDENLY CHANGED COLOR,
INDICATING AN EVENT UPSTREAM.
THE CREW HAS NO CHOICE
BUT TO EVACUATE.
WHAT'S THAT?
ALL RIGHT.
GO AHEAD, MAN.
YEAH, MAN.
WE GOT TO GO.
WE GOT TO GO ACROSS THE BRIDGE.
WE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE.
Dustin: SO WE HAD TO BACK OUT.
LOOKING PRETTY BAD.
RATHER SAFE THAN DEAD.
YEAH.
THAT THING HAS TOTALLY TURNED
TO CHOCOLATE MILK OUT THERE.
BUT IT IS NOT
GOOD RIGHT NOW.
IT IS NASTY LOOKING.
I'M LOOKING FOR TREES
AND DEBRIS,
OR, UH, A DRAMATIC
DROP IN THE WATER.
THAT MEANS BAD,
BAD STUFF FOR US.
I WENT FROM BEING ABLE
TO SEE TO ABSOLUTE BLACKNESS.
I'M -- I'M USED TO NOT
BEING ABLE TO SEE.
BUT I'VE NEVER SEEN THE CREEK
CHANGE SO DRAMATICALLY SO QUICK.
IT SCARES THE HELL OUT OF ME.
LET'S GO.
Narrator:
WITH LIVES ON THE LINE,
DUSTIN CANCELS DIVING
FOR THE REST OF THE DAY.
Dustin: I'M GONNA WAIT UNTIL
THE DANGER IS OVER WITH
BEFORE WE GET BACK
IN THAT WATER.
Narrator:
THE ONLY WAY TO INVESTIGATE
WHAT HAPPENED UPSTREAM
IS BY AIR.
HOW YOU DOING THERE, JACK?
HELLO, GENTLEMEN.
HOW ARE YOU?
ALL RIGHT.
GOOD TO SEE YOU, MAN.
THANKS FOR ACCOMMODATING US.
YOU BET YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
SO I WAS DIVING.
AND THE WHOLE CREEK WENT BLACK.
SO WE KIND OF FEEL LIKE
THERE'S SOMETHING
HAPPENING UPCREEK
FROM US RIGHT NOW.
AND I DON'T KNOW
HOW DANGEROUS IT IS.
Fred: WELL, WE'RE ABOUT HALF
A MILE UP THE CREEK, AREN'T WE?
THERE'S OUR WALKWAY RIGHT THERE.
YEP.
LOOKS LIKE EVERYTHING'S
STILL IN PLACE.
Fred:
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT UP THERE?
WHERE'S THE RIVER?
WHERE'S THE CREEK?
LANDSLIDE.
IT'S COMPLETELY
ACROSS THE CREEK.
HOLY COW.
OH.
OH, WOW.
NO WAY.
LOOK AT THIS, MAN.
THAT WHOLE THING
CAME DOWN OFF
THE SIDE OF THE MOUNTAIN
RIGHT THERE.
WOW.
WHAT WE'RE SEEING
RIGHT NOW,
THE WATER'S RUNNING UNDERNEATH
THIS LANDSLIDE, RIGHT?
SO IF THIS THING CLOGS UP,
THEN THERE'S A POTENTIAL
WE COULD GET, UH, LIKE, UH...
BIG COLLAPSE.
INLAND TSUNAMI.
Narrator: A MASSIVE LANDSLIDE
HAS COVERED THE CREEK.
THE WATER IS RUNNING BENEATH
IN A 200-YARD-LONG TUNNEL.
AT ANY TIME,
THIS COULD COLLAPSE,
DAMMING THE CREEK
AND TRAPPING MILLIONS
OF GALLONS OF WATER.
IF THE DAM SUDDENLY BREAKS,
A FAST-MOVING TIDAL
WAVE WILL RACE DOWN THE CANYON
TOWARDS THE MINE SITE,
OBLITERATING ANYTHING
AND EVERYONE
IN ITS PATH.
Dustin:
IF THIS COMES OVER THE TOP
OF THAT AND BUSTS THROUGH,
IT WILL KICK OUR ASS.
I THINK WHAT WE'RE GONNA
HAVE TO DO, REALLY,
IS ADVANCE INTO THE WATER
WITH, LIKE, EXTREME PREJUDICE.
IT DROPS DOWN TWO INCHES,
EVERYBODY OUT, NO EXCEPTIONS.
Narrator:
TWO HOURS LATER, THE WATER
COLOR HAS RETURNED TO NORMAL.
BUT DUSTIN IS SO CONCERNED
BY THE THREAT
OF A CATASTROPHIC FLOOD,
HE CALLS OFF DIVING TO INSTALL
A NEW EMERGENCY ESCAPE ROPE.
Dustin: EVERY MINING CREW
THAT'S EVER BEEN HERE
HAS BEEN WASHED OUT BY THE RAIN
AND THE FLOODS,
EVERY ONE OF THEM.
THERE'S NO EXCEPTIONS.
OUR BIGGEST PROBLEM
IS WE'RE TRAPPED.
THERE'S NOT ENOUGH
GOLD DOWN THERE
FOR SOMEBODY TO DIE.
ALL RIGHT, FELLAS,
HUDDLE UP REAL QUICK.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS.
WE'VE GOT
AN EVACUATION PLAN.
UH, THERE'S THE ROPE
THAT GOES UP.
WE GOT TO SCRAMBLE UP THIS --
THIS BIG CLIFF RIGHT HERE.
IF THE WATER CHANGES
TWO INCHES IN FIVE MINUTES,
I AM YANKING
EVERYBODY OUT.
AND THEY WILL BE
RUNNING UP A HILL.
YOU'RE GOING UP THERE.
AND YOU'RE GONNA
GET UP THERE FAST.
I DON'T CARE HOW OLD
OR TIRED YOU ARE.
YOU'RE JUST GETTING UP
THAT HILL.
MOTHER NATURE IS IN CONTROL.
AND WE'RE JUST TRYING
TO READ THE SIGNS.
WE'RE ON HIGH ALERT.
SOMETHING'S UP THERE
STALKING IT.
IT'S BEEN FILLING UP
FOR TWO DAYS.
AND IT COMES THROUGH,
WE'RE ALL DEAD.
EVERYONE'S DEAD.
Narrator:
THE NEXT DAY, THERE'S BEEN
NO CHANGE IN THE WATER LEVEL.
DUSTIN CAN SAFELY RESUME
HIS DIVE PLAN TO TUNNEL
BENEATH THE DIVERSION.
WE'RE GONNA GO BACK DIVING.
I GOT HIGH HOPES, MAN.
THIS IS CRAZY.
IT MIGHT BE A CHANCE
TO MAKE GOLD TODAY.
ALL HE'S GOT TO DO
IS GO DEEP ENOUGH.
Carlos: THERE'S CURRENT
COMING UNDERNEATH
THAT GOD DANG DIVERSION.
YOU CAN SEE IT
BUBBLING UP RIGHT THERE.
YOU CAN SEE IT BUBBLING UP.
YEAH. I DON'T THINK
OUR DIVERSION
IS DOING TOO MUCH RIGHT NOW.
Narrator: UP AHEAD...
THERE'S ACTUALLY SOMETHING IN
THERE THAT LOOKS LIKE A NUGGET.
IT'S BRIGHTER THAN
EVERYTHING ELSE.
IT'S SHINY.
YEAH!
Dustin: A LOT OF ROCKS
AND A LOT OF DIRT TODAY.
IT'S PROBABLY
OUR BEST DAY YET.
♪♪
Narrator: DUSTIN HAS UNDERMINED
THE DIVERSION
WHILE DIGGING HIS TUNNEL.
THE BOARDS BECAME LOOSE
AND BROKE FREE,
ALLOWING THE FIERCE CURRENT
TO RUSH INTO THEIR DIVE POOL.
IT LOOKS PRETTY BAD
FROM UP HERE
BECAUSE IT'S
BOILING UP EVERYWHERE.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE COMES PAUL.
HE'S COMING ALL THE WAY
TO THE MIDDLE NOW.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT. HE'S POUNDING THAT
FIRST ONE IN.
GOT AS MANY OF THOSE
BOARDS KNOCKED DOWN
AS THAT WOULD GO DOWN.
ALL RIGHT.
YEAH.
THAT'LL BE GOOD.
Dustin: UH, YEAH.
THE CURRENT WAS SO STRONG.
I'D REACH OUT AND GRAB
ONE OF THE BOARDS,
AND MY FEET WOULD
STICK STRAIGHT OUT
BEHIND ME LIKE SUPERMAN.
IT JUST STARTED WEARING ME
OUT WITH THE CURRENT
AND, UH, BREATHING REALLY HARD.
I COULD FEEL IT JUST
KICK MY BUTT.
Narrator:
PAUL HAS CALMED THE WATER
BY FIXING THE DIVERSION.
HE CAN NOW EXCAVATE THE SITE.
Paul:
I'VE GOT GOOD, CLEAR WATER,
PROBABLY THE CLEAREST WATER
I'VE SEEN SO FAR
SINCE I'VE BEEN DIVING HERE.
BUT IF I CAN GET
UNDERNEATH THAT DIVERSION,
SEE IF WE CAN'T GET UP
TO WHERE DUSTIN WAS AT,
THINK WE'LL DO
PRETTY GOOD TODAY.
WE'LL GET SOME GOLD.
THANK YOU.
IF YOU VALUE YOUR PINKIES,
YOU'LL FIND ME SOME GOLD.
[ LAUGHS ]
Dustin: ALL HE'S GOT TO DO
IS GO DEEP ENOUGH
AND FAR ENOUGH UPSTREAM,
AND WE'LL GET GOLD.
LOOKS GOOD?
YEP.
YOU LOOK GOOD.
RIGHT NOW, WE'RE JUST
WORKING TOWARDS UPCREEK.
WE'RE NOT SURE
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN
WHEN WE REACH THAT
DIVERSION RIGHT THERE.
ONCE WE GET UP TO THAT POINT,
WE'VE NEVER ACTUALLY
DONE THAT BEFORE.
BUT WHAT WE'RE LOOKING FOR IS
TO GET AS DEEP AS WE CAN
AND AS FAR UPCREEK
AS WE CAN TO SEE HOW THIS GOES.
YOU'RE ON THE RIGHT SPOT.
COMING UP.
Narrator: AN HOUR INTO THE DIVE,
PAUL HAS DUG DEEP ENOUGH
TO BEGIN DREDGING
BENEATH THE DIVERSION,
CLOSE TO WHERE DUSTIN
FOUND THE NUGGET.
IN THESE POCKETS
THAT ARE DOWN THERE,
WE HOPE CARRY SOME SORT OF GOLD.
PAUL'S MOVING A LOT
OF DIRT TODAY,
ESPECIALLY IN THE RIGHT SPOT.
IT'S WHAT GOLD MINING'S
ALL ABOUT.
HEY, THERE'S ACTUALLY
SOMETHING IN THERE
THAT LOOKS LIKE A NUGGET.
IT'S BRIGHTER THAN
EVERYTHING ELSE.
HOLD ON.
I THINK FRED IS SAYING
THAT THE STUFF
IN THE BOX LOOKS BRIGHT.
IT'S SHINY.
HE'S SAYING THAT
IT LOOKS LIKE GOLD.
Paul: YEAH!
Narrator:
AFTER 5 HOURS OF DREDGING,
PAUL HAS RUN EIGHT YARDS
OF PAY THROUGH THE SLUICE.
MOVED A LOT OF ROCKS
AND A LOT OF DIRT TODAY.
IT'S PROBABLY OUR BEST DAY YET.
UNFORTUNATELY,
IT'S JUST A ROCK.
Dustin: CLEANOUT.
HOW YOU DOING, MAN?
GOOD DIVE.
Narrator: THE CREW PULLS
THE MATS FOR A CLEANUP.
HOLY MOLY.
THAT'S A LOT OF GRAVEL, BRO.
Wes: YEAH.
THIS IS ALL THE MATERIAL
THAT CAME OUT
OF THE DREDGE ITSELF.
IF WE PICKED UP ANY GOLD
OVER THESE FEW DAYS,
IT'LL BE IN HERE.
THERE'S A LITTLE BIT
OF GOLD IN THE SLUICE.
AND WE'RE GONNA GO AHEAD
AND TAKE IT BACK TO PAN IT.
Narrator:
THEIR GOLD TOTAL SO FAR
IS JUST OVER HALF AN OUNCE.
TO BREAK EVEN BEFORE
THE END OF THE SEASON,
THEY NEED 42.
BACK AT CAMP,
WES CLEANS UP THE GOLD
FROM THE UPSTREAM SECTION
OF THE DIVE POOL.
Wes: WELL, I'VE GOT ALL OF
OUR SEASON'S GOLD
IN THIS CAN SO FAR.
THAT'S EVERYTHING THAT
WE'VE COLLECTED UP TILL NOW.
I'M GONNA TAKE OUT AND, UH,
LET THE GUYS SEE IT.
Fred: COOL EVENINGS LIKE THIS,
GREAT TO HAVE
A LITTLE FIRE OUT THERE.
HEY, LOOK. HEY.
WHAT'S HAPPENING, VOLE?
WELL, I GOT OUR TOTAL
FOR EVERYTHING
THAT WE'VE DONE
SO FAR FOR THE YEAR.
WHAT YOU GOT GOING?
THAT'S IT RIGHT THERE.
OH, LORD.
LITTLE UNDER AN OUNCE,
PROBABLY.
ABOUT THREE QUARTERS.
WOW, PRETTY SAD.
PRETTY, PRETTY SAD.
ONLY REASON WHY IT'S THAT MUCH
IS BECAUSE OF THAT NUGGET.
IF IT WASN'T FOR THAT NUGGET...
Dustin: WHICH IS CRAZY.
WE PULLED THAT NUGGET
RIGHT OFF THE TOP.
AND IT'S CRAZY THAT WE'RE NOT
SWIMMING IN GOLD RIGHT NOW.
Fred: MORE THAN HALF
THE SEASON'S GONE.
I MEAN, BASICALLY, WE GOT LESS
THAN AN OUNCE OF GOLD.
IT'S JUST TEASING US.
THAT'S ALL THAT'S DOING.
I THINK WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO DO
SOMETHING QUITE DIFFERENT,
RADICALLY DIFFERENT.
WOULD THOUGHT BY NOW
WE'D HAVE OVER
100 OUNCES THIS WHOLE THING.
BUT HERE WE'RE
SITTING ON NOTHING.
I MEAN, NOTHING.
CAN'T THINK ABOUT
QUITTING RIGHT NOW.
WE'VE GOT TOO MUCH
INVESTED INTO THIS.
♪♪
Fred: I'M LOOKING FORWARD
TO THE BIG DAY.
LOOKING FORWARD TO A GOOD LIFE
WITH A GOOD WOMAN.
Narrator:
FRED IS GETTING MARRIED
FOR THE FOURTH TIME
AFTER HIS LAST WIFE PASSED.
A LOT OF PEOPLE KNOW THAT I
WAS MARRIED FOR A LONG TIME.
UH, LORAINE WAS
THE LOVE OF MY LIFE
FOR THE LAST, UH, 20 YEARS.
WE HAD A GOOD MARRIAGE.
I LOVE YOU, FRED.
LOVE YOU TOO, HON.
THE LAST 4 MONTHS OF HER LIFE,
UH, I WAS HER
24-HOUR-A-DAY CARETAKER.
SHE, UH, FINALLY PASSED AWAY.
AND, UH, BUT LIFE GOES ON.
I THINK JEN AND I WILL MAKE
A, UH, VERY GOOD COUPLE.
THE ONLY COLD FEET
I'LL GET IS IN A DIVING SUIT.
[ LAUGHS ]
♪♪
Fred:
WELL, IT'S THE BIG DAY TODAY.
AM I READY FOR THIS?
HELL YES, I AM.
Narrator: 73-YEAR-OLD
FRED HURT IS
PREPARING
FOR HIS FOURTH WEDDING.
I'VE DECIDED THAT, UH,
I LIKE BEING MARRIED.
FOR ME, IT'S A GOOD THING.
I ACTUALLY MET JEN ONLINE,
FACEBOOK BASICALLY.
AND THAT'S HOW
WE REALLY MET.
SHE'S A FINE YOUNG WOMAN,
A LITTLE BIT OF A MAY,
DECEMBER SITUATION.
UM, SHE'S FINE
WITH THAT SITUATION.
I'M FINE WITH THAT SITUATION.
THAT'S WHAT COUNTS,
THAT WE'RE HAPPY.
I'M READY TO GO GET HITCHED.
Narrator: FRED IS 26 YEARS
OLDER THAN JEN.
LAST MINUTE PREP.
ALL READY TO GO.
Narrator:
THEY MAY HAVE MET ONLINE.
BUT JEN IS OLD SCHOOL
ABOUT HER FOOTWEAR.
Jen: SOMETHING BLUE.
[ LAUGHS ]
I PUT SOME BLUE LACES
ON MY XTRATUFS.
AND I DON'T WANT HEELS.
SO WE'RE LUCKY TO HAVE FOUND
EACH OTHER WHEN WE DID.
WE HAVE A LOT OF FUN,
MAKE EACH OTHER LAUGH.
SO FINALLY.
WE'RE OUT OF HERE.
♪ I WOKE UP SO EARLY
IN THE MORNING ♪
Narrator:
FRIENDS AND FAMILY HAVE FLOWN
IN FROM ALL OVER AMERICA.
YOU'RE LOOKING GOOD.
INCLUDING
FRED'S OLDEST DAUGHTER, DARLA.
LOOKING SHARP.
YEAH. YOU, TOO.
BEEN SO LONG
SINCE I HAD A TIE ON.
I HAD TO LOOK ON THE INTERNET,
SEE HOW TO TIE IT,
MAKE SURE I DID IT RIGHT.
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU DID PRETTY GOOD.
YOU LOOK GREAT, AWESOME.
Dustin:
I'M GETTING NERVOUS.
THIS IS DANIELLE.
HI.
THIS IS MY WOMAN.
I'M HAPPY FOR FRED.
IT SEEMS LIKE A REAL
NICE DAY FOR IT.
Narrator:
GOLD MINING LEGEND TONY BEETS
AND HIS WIFE, MINNIE,
HAVE TRAVELED 600 MILES
FROM THE KLONDIKE.
WHAT Y'ALL DOING DOWN HERE?
WELL, WE HAD TO COME
FOR THIS OCCASION.
I COULD IMAGINE.
THIS IS
MY OTHER SON, DARRYL.
Narrator: FRED'S OLDEST SON
IS A MINISTER.
THIS IS ACTUALLY
MY VERY FIRST WEDDING
AND MY MOST IMPORTANT.
AND, UH, REALLY LOOKING FORWARD
TO HONORING MY FATHER LIKE THIS.
ARE YOU READY?
YES.
Darryl: FREDERICK RICHARD HURT,
AKA DAD,
DO YOU HAVE THE GOLD,
RINGS THAT IS?
KNOCK IT OFF.
I PUT IT IN YOUR POCKET.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
GOLD.
WHO HERE KNOWS SOMETHING
ABOUT THAT STUFF?
WOULD LIKE MORE OF IT?
NO MATTER HOW MUCH GOLD
OR SUCCESS WE GAIN,
IT'S PRETTY EMPTY
WITHOUT SOMEONE CLOSE WITH WHOM
TO SHARE OUR LIVES,
OUR STRUGGLES,
SOMEONE YOU CAN REALLY TRUST.
THAT'S A REAL FIND.
AND I'M HAPPY FOR THEM.
DAD, YOU WANT TO GO FIRST?
JEN, I COMMIT MYSELF
COMPLETELY TO YOU.
AND I OFFER THIS RING...
...AS A SACRED SYMBOL
THEREOF.
I NOW INVITE YOU ALL TO JOIN ME
FROM NOW FORWARD,
TO RECOGNIZE THESE TWO AS ONE,
IN CALLING THIS COUPLE
MR. AND MRS. FRED AND JEN HURT.
YOU MAY KISS YOUR BRIDE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Dustin: IT'S REALLY COOL HAVING
A FAMILY TOGETHER
AND SEEING FRED HAPPY.
IT'S AWESOME.
Fred: TEARS OF HAPPINESS.
I DON'T CRY OFTEN.
BUT, UH, JUST A LITTLE OVERCOME
WITH A LITTLE, UH,
EMOTION RIGHT NOW.
CAN'T BELIEVE I SEEN
THE OLD MAN CRY.
HE DOES HAVE EMOTION
IN THERE SOMEWHERE.
Fred: IT'S ALL HAPPY.
NOW IT'S TIME TO GO
GET MY REAL BLUE JEANS
ON AND MY WORK SHIRT ON.
I'M READY TO GO TO WORK.
OKAY.
WE'RE OFF TO AUSTRALIA, RIGHT?
I THINK OUR HONEYMOON'S
GONNA HAVE TO WAIT.
WE GOT TO GET BACK
TO GOLD MINING.
Narrator:
ON THE NEXT EPISODE...
Dustin: WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO IS
WE'RE GONNA TAKE THIS DIVERSION
AND STICK IT UP THERE.
STOP.
STOP, STOP.
THAT BOY, MAN.
FRED.
FRED, DO YOU COPY?
BRING HIM UP.
HELP HIM OUT OF HERE.
HOLY [BLEEP].
THAT WAS A CLOSE CALL.
THERE IS GOLD IN HERE.
WHAT?
THERE IS GOLD.
[BLEEP] YEAH, IT'S GOLD.
DAMN RIGHT IT'S GOLD.
GET SOME, BROTHER.