**
Carlos: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S DO IT.
CRAZY [BLEEP]
Dustin: MAN,
YOU NEED TO HURRY UP.
I DON'T WANNA BE DOWN HERE
WHEN THAT WATER
COMES UP REAL HIGH.
OH, MY [BLEEP]
IT'S COMING UP!
GET OUT OF THERE!
Fred:
THERE'S NO MONEY LEFT.
IT COSTS MONEY
TO DO THESE THINGS.
OH, MY GOD!
EVERY SINGLE THING ON HERE
HAS BEEN SPENT
ON YOUR PROJECT.
DON'T EVEN GO THERE!
Dustin: I DON'T KNOW THAT I CAN
STILL WORK WITH HIM.
HOLY [BLEEP]
WOO, DOGGY!
OH [BLEEP]
THERE GOES OUR BOARD.
[ EXCITED CHATTER ]
-[BLEEP] BRIDGE IS GONNA GO!
-GET OUT! GET OUT!
DUDE,
CHECK THIS OUT.
THAT'S FROM PAUL'S LAST DIVE.
THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
HE MUST'VE
TOUCHED BEDROCK.
IT'S AWESOME, MAN.
Dustin: IN THE NEXT 2
TO 3 DAYS,
WE'LL KNOW WHETHER WE'RE RICH
OR WE JUST WASTED A LOT OF TIME.
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
DISCOVERY COMMUNICATIONS
**
PAUL,
I'M GONNA GET IT STARTED.
CHECK THE FUEL,
PLEASE.
WHATEVER WE GOT LEFT IN FUEL IS
HOW LONG WE'RE GONNA GET TO RUN.
LOOKS LIKE ABOUT
ANOTHER WEEK.
AND WE'RE GONNA BE DONE.
TIME IS NOT ON
OUR SIDE RIGHT NOW.
Narrator: AS THE DAKOTA BOYS
APPROACH THE END
OF THEIR MINING SEASON,
THEY'RE RUNNING ON FUMES.
THEY CAME TO FIND
MILLIONS IN GOLD.
FOURTEEN WEEKS LATER,
THEY'VE DREDGED JUST
A SINGLE OUNCE.
WELL, WE'RE GETTING
REALLY CLOSE TO THE END
OF OUR SEASON RIGHT NOW.
WE NEED TO FOCUS ON
GETTING DOWN TO THE BEDROCK.
IF WE DO NOT REACH THE BOTTOM,
WE WILL NOT EVEN HAVE
5 OUNCES OF GOLD.
Dustin:
IF I DON'T GO TO BEDROCK,
I'M CHEATING MYSELF
'CAUSE EVERY BOOK I'VE READ
ABOUT THIS PLACE,
EVERY JOURNAL,
EVERY CAPTAINS LOG,
ALL THE GOLD IS ON THE BEDROCK,
EVERYTHING HERE.
I STOP 10 INCHES
SHORT OF BEDROCK,
I MAY HAVE MISSED OUT
ON THE BIG --
BIGGEST PAYDAY OF MY LIFE.
Narrator: SINCE THE ICE AGE,
TENS OF MILLIONS OF DOLLARS
IN GOLD HAS FLOWED
DOWN MCKINLEY CREEK.
BECAUSE IT'S SEVEN TIMES
HEAVIER THAN THE ROCKS,
THE GOLD SANK TO THE BOTTOM.
THE DAKOTA BOYS HAVE EXCAVATED
DOWN TO A DEPTH OF 10 FEET.
DUSTIN IS STAKING HIS SEASON
ON FINDING A MASSIVE DEPOSIT
OF GOLD WORTH MILLIONS
ON THE BEDROCK.
THAT'S A BEAUTIFUL PIECE
OF GOLD RIGHT THERE.
Narrator: LAST WEEK,
THEY FOUND A NUGGET.
Carlos: DUDE, THIS IS WHAT
WE'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR.
Narrator: NOW,
THE CREW ARE CONVINCED
THEY'RE JUST FEET
FROM THE BEDROCK BONANZA.
THAT NUGGET HAS
BROTHERS AND SISTERS.
Dustin:
RIGHT NOW, IT FEELS LIKE,
"GOTTA GET SOME GOLD."
IT'S TIME.
WE NEED SOME INSPIRATION.
AND THAT COMES
IN THE COLOR GOLD.
Fred: YOU GOT GOOD VISIBILITY.
WATER LOOKS CLEAR TODAY.
IT'S LOW.
SO YOU SHOULD HAVE
A PRETTY GOOD --
PRETTY GOOD CLUE
WHAT'S GOING ON DOWN THERE.
WE'LL SEE HOW MANY HOURS
I CAN PUT IN.
Carlos: ALL RIGHT.
WE GOTTA PUT THE LIGHTS ON.
YEAH,
YOU SHOULD BE GOOD.
**
Dustin: [BLEEP] DO THIS.
TIME TO DIG.
[ MOTOR WHIRRING ]
I'M LOOKING.
I'M LOOKING FOR THE GOLD.
Narrator: DUSTIN AND FRED
OWE TODD HOFFMAN $50,000,
THE MONEY THEY BORROWED
TO COVER THEIR RUNNING COSTS.
[BLEEP] DAMN.
Paul: YOU'RE WHAT?
FINALLY.
[ CHEERING ]
THIS IS WHAT WE'RE LOOKING FOR.
THAT'S A PERFECT GOLD CACHE.
Narrator: JAGGED BEDROCK ACTS
AS A NATURAL SLUICE BOX,
TRAPPING GOLD
IN THE FRACTURES.
WHEN YOU'RE HOT,
YOU'RE HOT.
I BELIEVE THAT THAT HOLE
IS TOTALLY FILLED WITH GOLD.
WE COULD DREDGE THAT ALL OUT.
THERE'S GONNA BE A HANDFUL OF
NUGGETS AT THE END OF THE DAY.
Dustin:
IT'S ALL THE WAY ACROSS, TOO.
I THINK THERE'S GONNA BE
THE BIGGEST GOLD-CATCHING
RIFFLE AROUND HERE.
THERE'S -- THERE'S GONNA BE
SO MUCH GOLD SITTING THERE,
IT'S GONNA BE SILLY.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S CALM DOWN.
YEP. NOW, ALL YOU GOTTA DO IS
FIND THAT LITTLE POCKET OF GOLD.
LET'S DO THIS.
LOOK AT THAT.
WOO-HOO-HOO!
IT'S DIRTY, BROTHER.
POSSIBLY GOT SOME GOLD
IN HERE, BROTHER.
YEP, THAT'S TRUE. THAT'S WHAT
WE'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR.
Paul: GOD, I HOPE THERE'S SOME
GOLD IN THE BOX TODAY.
WE DEFINITELY NEED IT.
Fred: HEY.
IT'S A TREASURE HUNT, MAN.
Narrator: DUSTIN'S BEDROCK
DISCOVERY POWERS HIM ON
TO THE LONGEST
DIVE OF THE SEASON.
YOU'RE RIGHT AT 6 HOURS.
-WOO!
-A GOOD, LONG DIVE.
[BLEEP] MAN.
Carlos: WOO-HOO!
SIX HOURS!
WOO-HOO!
GOOD JOB, MAN.
SIX HOURS, MAN!
GIVE IT HELL,
DUSTIN.
GIVE IT HELL.
WE FOUND BEDROCK.
AND THERE'S A PERFECT V
AT THE BOTTOM,
JUST LIKE THAT,
ABOUT THAT WIDE.
UH, YOU CAN SEE
I BURNED THROUGH
ALMOST EVERY TIP
ON THE GLOVES.
WE FOUND BEDROCK.
IT'S ONLY 10 FEET
DOWN RIGHT THERE.
IF THERE'S GONNA BE ANY GOLD,
IT'S GOT TO BE THERE.
IT HAS TO BE.
OTHERWISE,
I'M IN BIG TROUBLE.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S CLEAN IT UP.
HOPEFULLY, WE GOT
DECENT GOLD IN IT.
GOT A LOTTA MATERIAL
MOVED TODAY.
WE JUST NEED TO RUN THAT STUFF
THROUGH OUR SMALL TROMMEL AND --
AND SEE WHAT'S ACTUALLY IN IT
AND THEN, UH,
GO FROM THERE.
DUSTINGS PUT IN
A PRETTY GOOD DAY, FOR SURE.
Dustin: A PRETTY GOOD DAY?
A PRETTY GOOD DAY?
IT WAS A GREAT DAY TODAY.
SIX AND A HALF HOURS,
I FOUND BEDROCK.
IT WAS A PRETTY
GOOD DAY?
THIS [BLEEP] GUY.
WHOO!
WE FOUND BEDROCK!
Narrator:
WES RUNS THE CONCENTRATE
FROM DUSTIN'S EPIC DIVE
TO SEPARATE OUT
THE BEDROCK GOLD.
ALL THE GOLD, THE MAJOR GOLD,
IN THIS CREEK IS FLAT DOWN
ON THE BEDROCK.
I THINK THAT'S GONNA GIVE US
A GOOD STREAK OF GOLD
DOWN THERE,
GOOD-SIZED CHUNK STUFF.
I'M HOPING TO SEE A FEW NUGGETS.
THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
Wes: DUSTIN.
Dustin: HOW MUCH
DID WE ACTUALLY GET?
THERE'S NOTHING. I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON.
I EXPECTED TO START GETTING
SOME FLAKES AND THIS AND THAT.
AND IT'S ALL THAT
SAME TINY [BLEEP]
THAT'S ALL
WE'RE [BLEEP] GETTING.
NO GOLD.
[BLEEP]
Narrator: DUSTIN'S BEDROCK
IS A BUST.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT SPOT
IN THE BEDROCK
DIDN'T YIELD
SOME SORT OF PAYMENT.
IT'S A PERFECT GOLD CACHE.
IT'S BAFFLING.
THIS SHOULD
BE JUST LOADED.
THAT'S JUST THE SADDEST
THING EVER.
CAN'T WIN HERE.
I CAN'T WORK
ANY HARDER.
I'M NOT GONNA GET
ANY SMARTER.
I JUST PUT SO MUCH MONEY
INTO THIS PLACE.
AND, I MEAN,
AT THIS POINT,
I OWE --
PRETTY MUCH OWE EVERYBODY.
IF I GO THROUGH
THIS WHOLE SEASON
WITHOUT FINDING GOLD,
I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN DO THIS ANYMORE.
THE HEARTBREAK
IS JUST TOO MUCH.
WINTER IS ABOUT TO CALL TIME
ON THEIR SEASON.
AND THEY HAVE JUST
A SINGLE OUNCE OF GOLD,
$1,200 TOWARD THE $50,000
THEY OWE THEIR INVESTOR,
TODD HOFFMAN.
I HATE TO HAVE -- MAKE --
DO THIS, MAN.
I'M JUST GONNA HAVE TO CALL TODD
AND TALK ABOUT GOLD
OR THE LACK THEREOF,
CERTAINLY NOT SOMETHING
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO.
OH.
Narrator: TODD'S DUE
BOTH HIS INVESTMENT
AND A 15 PERCENT
CUT OF ALL THEIR GOLD.
[ CELLPHONE RINGS ]
TODD, THIS IS FRED.
YEAH.
[ SIGHS ]
RIGHT NOW, THERE IS NO GOLD,
VERY, VERY LITTLE.
I GOT AN EXCAVATOR.
I GOT THAT LOADER.
I GOT THE RESOURCES
TO GET YOU PAID BACK.
YOU WILL DEFINITELY BE PAID.
THE GOLD, NOT SO MUCH.
[ SIGHS ]
GOD.
I DON'T LIKE OWING PEOPLE.
I JUST NEVER THOUGHT
I'D COME TO THE POINT
THAT I'D HAVE TO SELL OFF
AN EXCAVATOR AND A LOADER.
Narrator: UP AHEAD...
DUDE, CHECK THIS OUT.
THAT'S FROM PAUL'S LAST DIVE.
THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
THAT'S AS MUCH GOLD AS
WE'VE MADE THIS ENTIRE SUMMER.
IT'S AWESOME, MAN.
WOO, DOGGY!
IT'S COMING UP!
OH [BLEEP]
THERE GOES OUR BOARD!
BRIDGE IS GONNA GO!
GET OUT!
Narrator:
THE DAKOTA BOYS ARE STARING
FAILURE IN THE FACE.
THE END OF THE SEASON
IS UPON THEM.
THEY HAVE NO GOLD
TO PAY OFF THEIR DEBTS.
Fred: YOU'RE TALKING
HINDSIGHT.
YOU'RE THE MONDAY NIGHT
QUARTERBACK.
YOU COULD'VE DONE THIS.
YOU COULD'VE BEEN --
-ARE YOU [BLEEP] KIDDING ME?
THERE'S NO MONEY LEFT.
-ARE YOU [BLEEP]
-I'M NOT KIDDING YOU ONE BIT.
AND I'M GONNA
TELL YOU WHAT.
YOU CAN TAKE THIS
AND SHOVE IT UP
YOUR [BLEEP]
-[BLEEP]
Narrator: FRED WAS IN CHARGE
OF THE FINANCES.
AND HE SPENT
EVERY LAST DIME.
Dustin: YOU DON'T
UNDERSTAND THAT!
I -- I HATE SEEING
FRED AND DUSTIN CLASH.
IT JUST CREATES --
IT CREATES
A LOT OF TENSION
THAT WE ACTUALLY DON'T NEED.
WE HAVE SO MANY
PROBLEMS OUT HERE
WITHOUT ALL THAT BULL [BLEEP]
NONE OF THOSE BILLS
HAVE BEEN PAID YET.
YOU ARE FULL OF [BLEEP]
OKAY.
WE NEED TWO TANKS
OF GAS OUT THERE.
WHO'S GONNA BUY 'EM?
I JUST AM --
JUST REMINDING
THAT IT COSTS MONEY
TO DO THESE THINGS.
OH, MY [BLEEP] FRED.
YOU KNOW,
YOU DON'T APPRECIATE
ANYTHING ANYBODY
HAS DONE FOR YOU.
A THOUSAND DOLLARS
AND SOME BILLS?
AND EVERY SINGLE THING
ON HERE...
-YOU CAN KISS MY ASS.
-...HAS BEEN SPENT
ON YOUR PROJECT.
MY PROJECT?
NOT EVERY DECISION
YOU MADE WAS GREAT,
AND NOT EVERY DECISION
OF MINE WAS THE BEST,
BUT IT WAS SPENT
ON YOUR PROJECT.
DON'T EVEN GO THERE.
**
TOTALLY UNREASONABLE.
IT'S THE WAY IT IS.
Dustin: I DON'T KNOW THAT I CAN
STILL WORK WITH HIM.
HAS NO UNDERSTANDING,
NO UNDERSTANDING OF BUSINESS,
NOT ONE CENT.
THE OPERATION'S
DEAD WITH MONEY.
BUT WE STILL GOT SOME FUEL.
AND WE STILL GOT THE GUYS
THAT ARE READY TO WORK
THEIR ASSES OFF.
WE CAN STILL
MAKE A BIG PUSH.
**
Narrator: FRED HAS BLOWN
THEIR BUDGET.
BUT THE DAKOTA BOYS
HAVE ENOUGH FUEL
FOR A FINAL 6 DAYS OF DIVING.
Dustin: I'M A VENGEFUL GUY.
I'M ANGRY.
WHEN I SEE HIM, IT'S GONNA BE
THE HARDEST THING IN THE WORLD
FOR ME TO GO, "YEAH,
COME ON DOWN. NO PROBLEM."
DUSTIN AND I HAVE BEEN,
UH, FEUDING, I GUESS YOU'D SAY,
FOR ABOUT THE LAST 4, 5, 6 YEARS
WE'VE BEEN OUT HERE.
PERSONAL STUFF KIND OF
GETS IN THE WAY SOMETIMES.
AND, IN THE HEAT OF BATTLE,
YOU SAY THINGS THAT YOU WISH
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE SAID.
BUT, UH, WE NEED TO,
UH, MOVE FORWARD,
FIND SOME, UH, COMMON GROUND TO,
UH, MAKE THIS THING,
THIS, UH, PROJECT A SUCCESS.
KINDA --
KINDA AWKWARDNESS, MAN.
THE AWKWARDNESS, MAN,
YOU CAN SLICE
WITH A GOD-DANG KNIFE, DUDE.
IF WE FINISH OFF TODAY
WITH NO YELLING AND NO DRAMA,
THEN IT SHOULD BE
A GOOD DAY, MAN.
Fred: HMM, HOLD UP.
GOT YOU SOMETHING.
[ CHUCKLES ]
-WHAT IS IT?
"SOMETIMES,
YOU MAKE ME CRABBY.
SOMETIMES,
YOU DRIVE ME NUTS."
"BUT WE STILL BELONG TOGETHER,
NO IFS, ANDS OR BUTS.
THE OLD MAN."
[ LAUGHTER ]
[BLEEP] DO I SAY
ABOUT THAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
YES, FRED'S BEING NICE.
Narrator: ON DUSTIN'S LAST DIVE,
HE FOUND BEDROCK
BUT ZERO GOLD.
NOW, FRED'S DIVING TO SEE
IF HE CAN SUCCEED
WHERE DUSTIN FAILED.
Fred:
I'M GONNA START OFF RIGHT THERE
AT THE END OF THE WALKWAY,
UH, ABOUT WHERE
THE BEDROCK IS.
CHECK IT OUT A LITTLE CLOSER
AND I'LL DETERMINE, UH,
WHAT DIRECTION TO GO FROM THERE.
WE'LL RUN IT DOWN
IN THERE FOR A LITTLE BIT.
WHOO! THAT IS COLD!
ALL RIGHT.
FRED, BACK UP CALM.
SO YOU WANNA GO
TO YOUR LEFT, SIR.
WE'VE GOT TO FIND
THAT GOLD STREAK.
WE'RE GETTING TOO CLOSE
TO THE END OF THE SEASON.
I MEAN, IT'S JUST...
IF WE CAN'T GET
TO THE PAY STREAK,
IT'S BEEN A WASTE OF A SEASON.
Carlos: YOU -- YOU'RE LOOKING
TO START AT THE WALL, RIGHT?
Fred: YEAH.
GOOD DEAL, FRED.
GOOD DEAL.
FIND US SOME GOLD,
PLEASE.
HAVE YOU SEEN ANY SIGN
OF THAT BEDROCK
THAT DUSTIN'S BEEN
TALKING ABOUT?
ROGER.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GOTTA RIP IT OFF.
-THERE YOU GO.
-THERE WE GO.
-GOOD DEAL, FRED.
GOOD DEAL.
WHAT'S UP?
THERE AIN'T NO DAMN
BEDROCK THERE YET.
THIS WAS DOWN AT THE VERY BOTTOM
OF WHEN I WENT DIGGING.
WHAT YOU GOT, MAN?
THIS STUFF RIGHT HERE,
YOU WOULD, UH,
PROBABLY
CALL THAT FALSE
BEDROCK RIGHT THERE.
IT IS MATERIAL THAT
IS CEMENTED TOGETHER.
I'M GONNA TAKE
YOUR WORD FOR IT, MAN,
'CAUSE I REALLY
DON'T KNOW.
Narrator:
OVER TIME, PRESSURE CAN
SOLIDIFY SEDIMENT AND GRAVEL
INTO A LAYER OF HARDPACK,
ALSO KNOWN AS FALSE BEDROCK.
BETWEEN THE HARDPACK
AND TRUE BEDROCK,
THERE CAN STILL BE
A MASSIVE DEPOSIT OF GOLD.
I WOULD EXPECT BEDROCK TO BE
JUST LESS THAN
A COUPLE OF FEET AWAY
FROM THAT RIGHT THERE.
Dustin:
THAT'S PRETTY AWESOME, DUDE.
IT'S A GREAT THING THAT
WE'RE FINDING FALSE BEDROCK.
I CAN'T SEE IT BEING
MORE THAN 12 INCHES DEEP.
WHEN WE GET TO THE REAL BEDROCK,
I HOPE IT'S JUST CHOCK FULL
OF THOUSANDS OF YEARS OF GOLD.
WE REALLY,
REALLY NEED TO SEE IT.
OH,
YOU'RE SO SILLY.
**
Dustin: IN THE NEXT 2 TO 3 DAYS,
WE'LL KNOW WHETHER WE'RE RICH,
OR WE JUST WASTED A LOT OF TIME.
Narrator: FRED'S DISCOVERED
A PROTECTIVE LAYER OF HARDPACK.
AFTER STRUGGLING FOR 15 WEEKS,
THE DAKOTA BOYS COULD BE
INCHES AWAY FROM VICTORY.
YOUR DIVE IS
THE MAKE-OR-BREAK DIVE.
THIS IS IT RIGHT HERE.
TODAY IS WHAT WE'VE
BEEN WORKING FOR.
YOU'RE GONNA FIND OUT HOW HARD
THAT HARDPACK REALLY IS.
I CAN'T SEE IT BEING
MORE THAN 12 INCHES DEEP.
AND WE HAVE TO
BUST THROUGH IT.
THIS IS THE ONLY DIG
I'VE EVER HAD
WHERE I THINK THERE
IS GOLD IN THAT SPOT.
IF YOU CAN GET DOWN THERE
AND CLEAN THIS OUT,
WE'RE GONNA GET PAID.
GET IT DONE, MAN.
OKAY.
I GOT THIS, MAN.
Narrator:
DUSTIN'S CONVINCED THAT,
IF PAUL CAN BREAK THROUGH
A FEW INCHES OF HARDPACK,
HE'LL HIT A MONSTER PAYDAY
SITTING ON THE TRUE BEDROCK.
BROUGHT A SPECIAL TOOL TODAY.
SO, HOPEFULLY, I CAN BUST
THROUGH THE BOTTOM WITH THAT.
I KNOW I CAN PRY BETWEEN ROCKS
AND GET STUFF OUT LIKE THAT.
SO THAT'S WHAT I'M GONNA DO.
Narrator: FUEL RESERVES ARE DOWN
TO 5 DAYS.
THE SUCCESS OF THE CREW
RESTS ON PAUL'S DIVE.
Dustin: THE SEASON'S
BEEN PRETTY CRAPPY.
I'D LIKE TO MAKE IT A POSITIVE,
NOT A NEGATIVE,
AND FIND ME SOME GOLD, MAN.
Paul: YEAH, WE CAN'T BE
MORE THAN A --
A FOOT AWAY
FROM THE BEDROCK.
IT'S GOT TO BE CLOSE.
MAN, THIS [BLEEP]
EVEN LOOKS LIKE CONCRETE.
ALL RIGHT.
SO YOU CAN ACTUALLY SEE
WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE NOW, HUH?
YEAH.
WOW.
I THINK THAT WIGGLE PICK'LL
DEFINITELY HELPED.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, UH, HE'S RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
GAME ON.
TIME TO MOVE SOME DIRT.
Narrator:
PAUL USES THE WIGGLE PICK
TO BREAK OPEN THE HARDPACK
SO THEY CAN RUN IT
THROUGH THE SLUICE.
[ CLINKING ]
[BLEEP]
DAMN, THAT IS SOME HARD,
HARD [BLEEP]
I START HITTING ON IT.
AGAIN, I GOT
THE NOZZLE SPRAY DOWN.
I CAN SCRATCH.
BUT IT SUCKS IT UP...
OH, GOOD.
ALMOST INSTANTLY.
BY THE END OF THIS, WE SHOULD
BE EXPERTS AT BREAKING ROCK.
YEAH.
Carlos: LOOK AT ALL THAT.
LOOK AT ALL THAT [BLEEP]
THAT'S THAT HARDPACK CRAP.
YOU SEE THAT [BLEEP]
ALL THESE FREAKING ROCKS
STUCK TOGETHER.
DIFFERENT BALL GAME, MAN!
DIFFERENT BALL GAME!
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME LEFT,
UH, TO BE SCREWING AROUND.
THE SOONER WE CAN
GET THIS DONE, THE BETTER.
IT'S EXTREMELY SLOW-GOING.
OKAY.
SEE IF YOU CAN FIND
THAT BEDROCK FOR ME, MAN.
I SHOULD'VE GAVE YOU
A HIT OF JAMESON.
OH, I FORGOT ABOUT THAT.
HOW FAR INTO THE HARDPACK
DO YOU THINK YOU ARE, MAN?
MAN, LOOKING AT IT,
I DON'T KNOW WHERE IT'S --
THE TOP OF IT IS
OR WHERE I'VE GOTTEN
TO THE BOTTOM
OF THE HOLE.
WE'RE PROBABLY 3,
3 1/2 FEET NOW.
DAMN.
THIS IS SOME SERIOUS
HARDPACK.
HE THINKS HE'S 3 FEET
INTO THE HARDPACK
AND STILL NO BEDROCK.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT WE'RE...
WE'RE RUNNING
OUT OF TIME.
AND I'M NOT GETTING
ANY BREAKS HERE.
YOU'D SAY A COUPLE INCHES
EVERY 30 MINUTES
OR MAYBE 3 INCHES
EVERY 30 MINUTES?
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
WELL, THE HARDPACK MAY
ACTUALLY JUST STOP US.
IT'S LIKE CHIPPING
AWAY AT CONCRETE.
WE'RE NOT GONNA GET
THROUGH IT ALL THE WAY.
THIS IS IT, MAN.
PACK IT UP.
LET'S DO A CLEANUP,
SEE WHAT WE GOT IN THE BOX,
GET OUT OF HERE.
Narrator: THE THICK HARDPACK
IS PREVENTING THEM
FROM GETTING TO BEDROCK GOLD.
IF THEY END THE SEASON NOW,
THEY'LL HAVE JUST
A SINGLE OUNCE.
Wes: DUSTIN.
DUDE, CHECK THIS OUT.
WHAT YOU GOT, MAN?
MAN, THAT CAME OUT
FROM THE LAST DIVE.
YOU BELIEVE THAT [BLEEP]
THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
SO THAT'S
FROM JUST PAUL?
YEAH.
WOW.
THAT'S AS MUCH GOLD AS WE'VE
MADE THIS ENTIRE SUMMER.
YEAH.
HEY, GUYS,
COME CHECK THIS OUT!
WHAT'S GOING ON IN HERE?
Narrator: AN OUNCE OF GOLD
IS WORTH $1,200...
LOOK AT THAT.
WOW.
Narrator: AN IMPRESSIVE HAUL
FROM A SINGLE DIVE.
IT'S INCREDIBLE, MAN.
Carlos: THAT'S GOOD [BLEEP]
RIGHT THERE THEN, HUH?
SEE, THAT'S WHAT'S
COMING OUTTA THE HARDPACK.
-YEAH.
IF WE CAN GET THROUGH
THAT HARDPACK, DUDE,
THEN IT'S GONNA BE GOOD.
WE WERE RIGHT
ON TOP OF IT.
Narrator: IF THERE'S THIS MUCH
GOLD IN THE HARDPACK,
THERE COULD BE A MONSTER
DEPOSIT ON THE BEDROCK.
THAT PROVES WHERE WE'RE
GOING IS THE RIGHT PLACE.
I CAN'T WAIT TO GET BACK DOWN
AND START GETTING REAL GOLD.
WE WERE RIGHT THERE
ON IT, MAN.
WE GOT TO COME UP
WITH SOME TOOLS
AND SOME MORE STUFF
TO GET THROUGH THAT HARDPACK.
IT LOOKS WONDERFUL.
Narrator: THE DAKOTA BOYS
HAVE ONE LAST SHOT.
Dustin: THIS IS GONNA BE
A GAME CHANGER ON THE HARDPACK.
Narrator: DUSTINGS RAIDED
THEIR STORAGE UNIT
AND FOUND A TOOL THAT COULD
SALVAGE THEIR SEASON.
THIS IS MY LITTLE BABY
JACKHAMMER RIGHT HERE.
SO WE'RE GONNA USE
AIR COMPRESSION
AND, UH, SMASH THROUGH
THIS HARDPACK STUFF.
SHE SHOULD BE ABLE TO JUST,
BLAH, JUST STRAIGHT THROUGH IT.
BIG THINGS ARE
GONNA HAPPEN HERE.
Narrator: THE AIR CHISEL
IS A SIMPLE BUT EFFECTIVE TOOL.
COMPRESSED AIR PASSES
THROUGH A CLOSED VALVE
AND DOWN TO THE FRONT
OF THE CYLINDER.
THIS FORCES THE PISTON,
OR STRIKER,
BACK UP THE CYLINDER.
AS IT MOVES, IT PUSHES
AIR OUT THROUGH VENTS.
BUT, ONCE THESE
ARE BLOCKED,
THE STRIKER SQUEEZES
THE REMAINING AIR,
FORCING THE VALVE OPEN.
NOW, THE COMPRESSED AIR
RAMS THE STRIKER FORWARD,
HITTING THE CHISEL,
REVERSING THE CYCLE.
THIS ACTION CAN REPEAT UP
TO 4,000 TIMES PER MINUTE,
100 TIMES FASTER
THAN THE HAMMER.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET ON OVER THERE.
AND, UH, WE'LL SET THIS UP
AND, UH, GET GOLD.
Carlos: THIS IS, WHAT,
10 MINUTES, MAN.
FOURTH QUARTER, BRO.
YOU KNOW, WE'RE BEHIND --
A FEW BEHIND, ONE TOUCHDOWN.
Fred: WE'RE TRYING TO MAKE
THE LAST EFFORT
TO GET US SOME
GOOD GOLD DOWN THERE.
TRIED EVERY IDEA
WE CAN COME UP WITH.
I BELIEVE WE'LL STILL DO IT.
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
Carlos: HOLY [BLEEP] MAN.
LOOK, MAN.
SHE LOOK LIKE
SHE'S ON STEROIDS TODAY.
Narrator: DUSTIN AND CREW HAVE
JUST 4 DAYS OF FUEL LEFT
TO BREAK THROUGH
TO BEDROCK GOLD.
Dustin: OH, WELL, THAT WATER
LOOKS HORRIBLE.
Narrator:
AND THE TORRENTIAL RAIN
IS RAISING THE WATER
LEVEL AN INCH AN HOUR.
Dustin: FURIOUS WATER.
Fred: WHOO!
WET, WET, WET.
[BLEEP]
GOD DANG, BRO.
CAN'T CATCH A BREAK.
Dustin: ONE TO 2 INCH OF RAIN
WILL DO A LOT OF FLOODING,
THIS IS SUCH
A LARGE CACHE AREA.
IT'S NOT SO MUCH THE WATER.
THIS TYPE OF RAIN CAUSES
A BUNCH OF LANDSLIDES HERE.
IT'S TERRIFYING BECAUSE
IT BRINGS DEBRIS WITH IT.
THE TREES AND THE ROCKS
THAT COME WITH IT, UH, THIS --
THEY'RE TERRIFYING.
Narrator: THE LAST TIME
THEY HAD RAIN LIKE THIS...
WHAT THE HELL
IS THAT UP THERE?
LANDSLIDE. IT'S COMPLETELY
ACROSS THE CREEK.
...HALF A MOUNTAINSIDE SLID DOWN
AND BLOCKED THE CREEK.
THERE'S A POTENTIAL WE CAN GET
ON, LIKE, AN IN-LAND TSU--
TSUNAMI?
[ HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING ]
[ RAIN FALLING ]
DEFINITELY
IN THE DANGER ZONE.
IF IT'S RAINING AS MUCH UP
THERE AS IT IS DOWN HERE,
JUST COME DOWN HERE
AND JUST WRECK THIS STUFF, MAN.
THIS IS A SAFETY THING.
I'M MAKING A DECISION.
I DON'T THINK
WE'RE GONNA DIVE TODAY.
I KNOW IT'S OUR LAST PUSH.
AND, BELIEVE ME,
I WANNA BE DOWN THERE.
I WANNA BE DOWN THERE BAD.
BUT I DON'T
WANNA DIE DOING IT.
I AGREE.
THIS IS TOO DANGEROUS,
WAY TOO DANGEROUS
TO DEAL WITH THIS.
Fred: WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE OUGHTA DO HERE, DUSTIN?
WELL,
I'M WORRIED RIGHT NOW.
I -- I JUST --
I BELIEVE IT'S GONNA FLOOD.
AND I DON'T WANNA BE DOWN
IN THAT WATER IF IT FLOODS.
OKAY.
THEY'RE FORECASTING RAIN
FOR ANOTHER 2 DAYS STRAIGHT.
SO THIS IS
THE BEST THE WATER
IS GONNA BE
FOR THE NEXT 2 DAYS.
WE GOT JUST A LITTLE BIT
OF TIME LEFT.
I WANNA KEEP ON GOING
UNTIL I FIND
THE DEEPEST PART
OF THAT BEDROCK DOWN THERE.
I'M READY
FOR THAT DIVING JOB.
YOU CAN GO DOWN
IF YOU WANT.
I AIN'T STOPPING YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S SEE WHAT WE CAN DO.
YOU WANNA HELP HIM?
Carlos: YEP.
Narrator: 73-OLD FRED
IS GONNA BRAVE
THE RAGING CREEK
IN A LAST-DITCH ATTEMPT
TO HIT BEDROCK GOLD.
Fred: I'M HOPING THAT DIVERSION
HOLDS OUT ALL RIGHT.
UH, WE'RE IN PRETTY
GOOD SHAPE RIGHT NOW
IF THE WATER STAYS BELOW
ABOUT 2 TO 3 FEET.
IT COMES UP MORE
THAN THAT, GAME IS OVER.
Dustin: IF IT KEEPS
RAINING LIKE THIS,
WE'RE GONNA END UP
WITH SOME SORTA HIGH WATER.
THE WATER'LL COME UP SO FAST.
IT CAN BE A BIG PROBLEM FOR US.
Wes: THAT WOULD BE
THE END OF HIM.
SO WHAT WE DO IS WE --
WE TAKE A LOT OF PRECAUTIONS.
SO LET'S GET HIM UNDER.
LET'S GET HIM SET UP.
SO LET'S JUST BE
THINKING 'BOUT IT.
**
Narrator:
THE CREW PREPS THE LATEST WEAPON
IN THEIR WAR ON HARDPACK.
LOOK AT THAT!
THAT LOOKS COOL.
SHE WORKS.
IT'S INTERESTING
WITH WORKING WITH FRED
BECAUSE, UH, THIS IS
JUST SOME CRAZY WATER.
I CAN'T EVEN BELIEVE
WE'RE TRYING IT.
Carlos: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S DO IT.
CRAZY [BLEEP] YOU.
Dustin: MAN,
YOU NEED TO HURRY UP.
I DON'T WANNA BE DOWN HERE
WHEN THAT WATER
COMES UP REAL HARD.
Carlos: [ LAUGHS ]
Fred: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S MAKE SOME GOLD.
TODAY'S THE DAY, FELLAS.
MAN, THAT CHIPPER'S GONNA KNOCK
THE HELL OUTTA THIS STUFF.
WOW.
YEAH.
HOLD IT.
ALL RIGHT.
WE GOT IT.
I HIT THE BEDROCK.
GOOD JOB, MAN.
Narrator: FRED'S DECISION
TO DIVE HAS PAID OFF.
HE'S BROKEN THROUGH
THE HARDPACK.
HE CAN FINALLY GET
TO THE BEDROCK GOLD.
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
WATCH THE WATER LEVEL.
WATER CAME UP 2 INCHES
IN 5 MINUTES.
WE GOT DEBRIS EVERYWHERE.
OH, MY [BLEEP]
HERE IT COMES.
IT'S COMING UP!
WHOO, DOGGY!
LOOK AT THAT [BLEEP]
HOLD ON!
LET'S ABORT!
UH, ABORTING ALL DIVE, FRED.
ABORT DIVE.
GOTTA GO, FRED!
HOLY COW.
MAN, IT'S COMING
OVER THE GOD DANG...
[ INDISTINCT EXCITED CHATTER ]
GET HIM OUT OF THERE!
**
Narrator: A MILE AWAY
UP AT CAMP,
FRED'S NEW WIFE, JEN,
KNOWS THAT FRED'S DIVING
IN THE RAGING CREEK.
UH, I'M A LITTLE SHOCKED
AT THE SITUATION.
YEAH, EVERY BIT OF ME
WANTS TO GO OVER THERE
JUST FOR MY OWN BENEFIT.
BUT HE'S A GROWN MAN.
IT'S UP TO HIM TO MAKE
HIS OWN DECISIONS.
Carlos: FRED!
Jen: FRED, DO YOU HAVE A COPY?
Dustin:
GET HIM OUT OF THERE!
**
Carlos: LET'S GO, FRED!
GOTTA GO!
Narrator: MCKINLEY CREEK
HAS RISEN
20 INCHES IN THE LAST 5 MINUTES.
73-YEAR-OLD FRED HURT
IS STILL IN THE WATER,
DESPERATE TO GET THE GOLD
THEY NEED LYING ON THE BEDROCK.
WE'RE IN A PICKLE.
COME ON!
WE GOTTA GET
THE [BLEEP] HERE!
GOTTA GO, FRED!
GO, GO, GO.
OVER THERE.
CAN YOU GET THAT STUFF?
I NEED HELP!
[BLEEP]
IT'S GOING UNDER!
IF DUSTIN LOSES THE DREDGE,
THEIR SEASON IS OVER.
HEY, YO, LINE IT UP!
I NEED SOME HELP!
YEAH! YEAH!
GET THIS PART OF THIS THING UP.
OH, OH, OH!
THIS IS WHAT KILLS
PEOPLE RIGHT HERE.
THIS IS HOW
YOU DIE MINING.
Narrator:
THE DREDGE IS SAFE.
BUT DUSTIN AND A CAMERAMAN
ARE ON THE WRONG
SIDE OF THE CREEK.
AND THE WATER IS STILL RISING.
[ RUMBLING IN DISTANCE ]
Carlos: YOU HEARD --
YOU HEARD THAT THUNDER?
THAT'S NOT THUNDER, MAN.
THAT'S THE ROCK.
THAT'S ALL THE ROCK
MOVING RIGHT.
Fred: HOLY COW.
DUSTIN,
WHAT YOU DOING?
HEY!
WHY DON'T YOU GET OVER HERE?
IT'S STARTING TO WASH
THIS SIDE OUT!
GO! GO! GET!
Carlos: HEY! MAN,
YOU'RE A [BLEEP] IDIOT, MAN?
GET THE [BLEEP]
OUTTA THERE, MAN.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
-I'M TAKING CHANCES, MAN.
-WHAT, YOU WANT SOMETHING FUNNY?
[BLEEP] MAN.
IT'S COMING OVER THE BACK GATE!
WATCH OUT!
OH [BLEEP]
THERE GOES OUR BOARD!
[ EXCITED CHATTER ]
-BRIDGE IS GONNA GO!
-GET OUT! GET OUT!
[ CHATTER ]
Carlos: WHOO!
[BLEEP]
[BLEEP] LOOK AT THAT.
MEAN DIRT.
MAN,
THAT CAME UP SO QUICK.
I MEAN,
WHAT, 5 MINUTES?
I JUST --
I'M IN DISBELIEF
THAT HAPPENED
SO [BLEEP] QUICK.
Carlos: I THOUGHT THAT WAS
THUNDER AT FIRST, MAN.
BUT THAT WAS ALL ROCK.
-YEP.
[BLEEP] [BLEEP]
THERE'S NOT GONNA
BE ANYTHING LEFT.
THE 15-FOOT HOLE
THAT WE JUST HAD,
ALL YOUR WORK, GONE,
ABSOLUTELY GONE.
Fred: THERE AIN'T
NO HOLE DOWN THERE.
BET IT'S NOT WORTH
5 FOOT DEEP RIGHT THERE.
YEAH, I BET YOU'RE RIGHT.
Narrator: IT TOOK 4 MONTHS
TO DIG DOWN TO BEDROCK GOLD.
BUT NOW, IN 5 MINUTES,
THEIR DIVERSION
HAS BEEN BLOWN AWAY.
THE STORM'S AFTERMATH
AND TORRENT
HAVE REFILLED THEIR HOLE.
GAME OVER.
Dustin: SORRY, GUYS.
I KNOW WE WERE CLOSE.
BUT, UH, THIS IS DONE, MAN.
WE'RE DONE.
WE AIN'T GONNA BE
DOING NO MORE WORK.
Carlos: YOU CAN'T MAKE UP
THIS KINDA [BLEEP] DUDE.
SWEAT AND BLOOD
FOR GOLD, FIND GOLD.
THE RIVER TAKES IT AWAY.
Dustin: ONE MINUTE,
THERE'S BEDROCK.
THE NEXT MINUTE,
EVERYTHING'S GONE.
IT'S A HORRIBLE WAY
TO END THE SEASON.
WE SHOULD BE ENDING
THE SEASON ROLLING IN GOLD.
BUT, INSTEAD, ALL OF
OUR WORK GOT WIPED OUT.
Narrator: WES HAS ONE LAST
SURPRISE FOR DUSTIN.
Wes: MAN, DUDE,
CHECK THIS OUT.
THAT'S FROM THAT
DIVE THAT FRED DID
BEFORE WE GOT FLOODED OUT.
LOOK AT THAT.
Dustin: NICE TO KNOW THAT
THERE'S BIG CHUNKY
GOLD SITTING DOWN THERE.
WE WERE RIGHT
THERE ON IT, MAN.
CHECK THIS OUT, GUYS.
DAMN.
WOW.
YOU WERE THERE.
WE WERE THERE.
WE FOUND IT.
I THINK THAT WAS ONLY,
LIKE, 30 MINUTES.
IF WE HEADED TO A PLACE
WHERE WE COULD DIG IN THAT
BOTTOM EVERY DAY,
YOU FOLLOW
THAT GOLD STREAK,
WE SHOULD HAVE 10 OF THESE
FULL OF GOLD, MAN.
-YEAH, WE'D HAVE KILLED IT.
-HOW'D IT LOOK OVERALL?
UH, LET ME GRAB IT.
GOOD JOB, GUYS.
THAT'S FREAKING AWESOME, BRO.
THAT'S FREAKING
BEAUTIFUL, BRO.
Richardson: WE'RE CLOSE, MAN.
WE'RE CLOSE.
BEAUTIFUL.
Narrator: ADDING
TO THIS WEEK'S CHUNKY
BEDROCK GOLD,
THE CREW SEES THE FRUITS
OF THEIR SEASON'S LABOR,
MORE THAN HALF OF WHICH
THEY MADE IN THE LAST FEW DAYS.
TWO AND A HALF OUNCES.
TWO AND A HALF OUNCES,
WORTH JUST $3,000
BUT PROOF THEY WERE
ON THE VERGE OF MILLIONS.
I KNOW IT'S NOT THAT IMPRESSIVE.
BUT WE GOT TO THE GOLD.
BUT WE DIDN'T RETRIEVE
ALL OF IT YET.
IT'S A SAD THING THAT WE
DIDN'T GET RICH THIS YEAR.
Fred:
BITTERSWEET, YOU KNOW.
HEY,
BUT THE MAIN THING HERE --
WHATEVER IS DONE THERE
IS STILL THERE.
WE NEED TO COME BACK
AND GET IT.
WE'LL GET IT
NEXT YEAR, FOR SURE.
WELL, I WILL BE STARTING MY
CONSTRUCTION JOB FOR THE WINTER.
AND I HOPE TO MAKE
ENOUGH MONEY TO START OVER.
ANYBODY FEEL LIKE COMING BACK,
EVEN THOUGH WE GOT 2 1/2 OUNCES?
NOW THAT WE SEE THE GOLD'S
GETTING BIGGER AND CHUNKIER,
I'LL BE HERE.
I'LL COME BACK.
YEAH, YOU'VE BEEN A REALLY,
REALLY GOOD PART
OF THIS GROUP, MAN.
I'LL COME BACK...
ON MY OWN TERMS.
OUR GOLD
IS STILL THERE, BOYS.
AT LEAST WE KNOW IT'S SAFE
DOWN -- DOWN THERE, RIGHT?
WE KNOW THAT THERE'S
GOLD DOWN THERE.
WE'RE NOT JUST HOPEFUL.
WE KNOW IT.
WE'VE PROVEN THAT THERE
IS GOLD DOWN THERE
AND A LOT OF IT.
WE JUST HAVEN'T
GOT TO IT YET.
AH, SO CLOSE.
**