DUSTIN, YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT THE
[BLEEP] YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
YOU DON'T KNOW ME.
YOU DON'T HAVE ANY [BLEEP] IDEA
OF WHAT I'VE BEEN THROUGH
AND WHAT I'VE DONE AND THE
EXPERIENCE THAT I [BLEEP] HAVE
AND WHAT I'VE SACRIFICED
TO GET TO THIS POINT
TO BE QUALIFIED TO BE HERE IN
THIS [BLEEP] CREW WITH YOU GUYS.
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
YOU'RE NOT QUALIFIED
TO BE IN THIS [BLEEP] CREW.
YOU'RE QUALIFIED TO...
ALL RIGHT. THEN, I'M DONE.
THEN I'LL LEAVE.
THEN BE GONE.
[ BLEEP ].
IT'S THAT [BLEEP] SIMPLE.
I'M OUT OF HERE.
GO. DO YOUR THING.
PICK UP ON THE FRONT END.
YOU'RE NOT EVEN
LINED UP YET.
DUSTIN, WHAT IS THE PROBLEM?
DON'T MAKE ME TAKE CHARGE.
I DON'T WANT TO.
I WANT TO INTRODUCE
YOU TO CARLA.
I'M A COMMERCIAL DIVER.
I WORK OFFSHORE OIL PLATFORM
FOR 15 YEARS NOW.
DON'T GO INTO THAT
[BLEEP] WHITEWATER.
THE WATER'S COMING UP RIGHT NOW.
OKAY,
YOU DON'T HAVE ANY AIR?
AH, [BLEEP].
UH-OH.
I SAW IT TOO.
I SAW IT.
UH-OH.
HOLY [BLEEP].
DAMN, LOOK AT ALL THAT
GOLD THAT'S IN THERE!
THE GOLD IS SITTING
ON THE SURFACE RIGHT NOW.
WE JUST FOUND IT.
WOO!
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
DISCOVERY COMMUNICATIONS
DON'T LET GO OF THE END
OF THAT ROPE.
THAT'S ALL.
DON'T FALL.
TRUST YOU, MAN.
Narrator: HIGH IN ALASKA'S
REMOTE CHILKAT MOUNTAINS,
THE DAKOTA BOYS
ARE WORKING ON THE TRAIL
BETWEEN THEIR CAMP
AND THE DIVE SITE.
WE'VE GOT A TREE THAT'S
HANGING OFF BY THE ROOTS,
STRAIGHT DIRECTLY
OVER OUR TRAIL.
IF IT FELL DOWN
AND HIT ANYBODY,
THAT WOULD BE
THE END OF SOMEBODY.
Dustin: OW.
WE NEED TO GET TO WORK.
HOPEFULLY IT ELIMINATES ONE
OF THE PROBLEMS THAT KILLS US.
IT SHOULD BE
STRAIGHT BELOW YOU.
THAT TREE LOOKS LIKE
IT'S HANGING OVER THE EDGE.
YEAH, I DON'T EVEN KNOW
IF I CAN GET DOWN TO IT.
THIS IS A LOT OF WORK.
IT REALLY BETTER PAY OFF.
UGH.
Narrator: DUSTIN AND HIS CREW
ARE CHASING A DREAM --
THAT THESE DEADLY
McKINLEY CREEK RAPIDS
HIDE SOME OF ALASKA'S
UNFOUND GOLD DEPOSITS --
PLUNGE POOLS BELOW THE SURFACE
THAT HAVE TRAPPED
MILLIONS IN GOLD.
THIS SEASON'S PRICE TAG,
$50,000 IN RUNNING COSTS.
SO THEY'LL NEED TO FIND
AT LEAST 42 OUNCES OF GOLD
BEFORE ANY OF THEM MAKES A CENT.
THE RACE IS ON TO FINISH
THEIR DIVE PLATFORM
AND START DREDGING FOR GOLD.
BUT FIRST, DUSTIN HAS TO
REMOVE THE DEAD TREE
THAT'S THREATENING
TO FALL ON THEM.
Dustin: LITERALLY STANDING ON
TOP OF THEM, I BELIEVE.
I CUT THIS LOOSE,
HOPEFULLY THERE'S NO
CHAIN REACTION
AND THINGS FALL ON ME.
COPY THAT.
CRAZY. IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I THINK THE WHOLE LITTLE LEDGE
IS GOING TO GO WHEN IT GOES.
COME LOOSE!
YEAH!
FINALLY.
THAT WAS A LOT HARDER THAN
I THOUGHT IT WAS GOING TO BE.
THANKS FOR CATCHING
MY BACK ON THAT ONE.
YOU CONQUERED IT, MAN.
HOLY COW.
WELL, THAT'S ONE LESS HEADACHE
WE HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT NOW.
YEAH, SO IT DOESN'T
KILL SOMEBODY.
NEXT STEP FOR DUSTIN, PAUL,
WES, AND GREENHORN ZACK --
HAUL THE LUMBER OVER
THE TREACHEROUS MILE-LONG TRAIL
BETWEEN CAMP
AND THE DIVE SITE.
ZACK, WHAT I NEED YOU TO DO
IS JUST TO GO UP
AND DOWN THAT HILL
OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
IT'S GOING TO BE
A LOT OF WALKING.
MAN, I THINK IT'D BE PERFECT
TO JUST THROW SOME TWO-BY-FOURS
IN BETWEEN THAT LITTLE GAP
ON MY HANDLEBARS
ON MY DIRT BIKE THERE
AND JUST SIT ON 'EM
AND RIDE 'EM UP THE HILL.
IT'S NOT SAFE ENOUGH
TO BE OVER THERE TO DO THAT.
YOU'D BE JOUSTING
WITH TREES AND STICKS.
CAN'T BE LAZY.
I JUST DON'T SEE HOW A SIMPLE
LITTLE IDEA TURNED INTO
ME NOT WANTING TO DO IT NOW
AND ME BEING LAZY.
I WAS JUST...
NO, NOT LAZY.
A LITTLE...
IT JUST OPENS YOU UP
FOR TOO MUCH.
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU KNOW HOW WE ARE.
YOU KNOW HOW WE ROLL.
[BLEEP]
WHEN THEY WRITE ME OFF INSTANTLY
WHEN I COME UP WITH AN IDEA,
IT REALLY FRUSTRATES ME
AND PISSES ME OFF.
ZACK'S ALWAYS TRYING TO FIND
THE EASY WAY, JUST LIKE FRED,
BECAUSE HE'S A MACHINE OPERATOR.
BUT OUT HERE,
IT TURNS INTO PHYSICAL,
HARD LABOR HAS TO HAPPEN.
LET'S SEE HOW
THAT WORKS OUT.
Narrator: 24-YEAR-OLD ZACK HAS
BEEN A LOGGER FOR EIGHT YEARS,
BUT THIS IS HIS
FIRST TIME MINING.
Zack: YOU KNOW,
I'M THE NEW GUY HERE.
I'M THE LOWEST
ON THE TOTEM POLE.
BUT IT IS HARD, ESPECIALLY
COMING FROM A POSITION
WHERE I WAS RUNNING
MY OWN CREWS
AND I HAD A LOT OF PEOPLE
WORKING UNDER ME TO WHERE NOW,
I'M WORKING UNDER
EVERYBODY ELSE.
I DON'T KNOW IF I'M
GOING TO BE ABLE
TO GET USED TO THAT, REALLY.
I'M GOING TO DO IT MY WAY,
THAT'S JUST ALL THEIR IS TO IT.
SO HERE I GO.
THIS [BLEEP] SUCKS.
Narrator:
OVER THE LAST 120 YEARS,
THE CREEKS AROUND
THE CHILKAT MOUNTAINS
HAVE PRODUCED MORE THAN
$100 MILLION WORTH OF GOLD.
MEN HAVE MADE THEIR FORTUNES
AND LOST THEIR LIVES.
THREE WEEKS AGO, THE DAKOTA BOYS
RETURNED FOR ANOTHER SEASON
TO FIND THEIR FORTUNES
DIVING FOR GOLD.
I THINK THAT'S GOING TO
MAKE YOU A WEALTHY MAN.
BUT FOUND ALL THEIR EQUIPMENT
HAD BEEN DESTROYED.
THE WATER MUST'VE
COME UP EIGHT FEET.
THERE AIN'T A THING LEFT.
FRED WAS FORCED TO
TAKE A $50,000 LOAN
FROM OLD RIVAL TODD HOFFMAN.
I WILL BE CHECKING IN.
NOW, FRED MUST DEAL
WITH THE CONSEQUENCES.
Fred: IF TODD HOFFMAN DOESN'T
HAVE ENOUGH FAITH IN ME
THAT HE HAS TO SEND
SOMEONE DOWN,
I DON'T KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT HIS BACKGROUND IS,
DON'T KNOW WHAT YOUR
QUALIFICATIONS ARE, AN OUTSIDER.
I GUESS IF I NEED MONEY,
I HAVE TO PUT UP
WITH CIRCUMSTANCES HERE.
YOU MUST BE CARLOS.
YES, SIR.
HOW YOU DOING?
FRED?
FRED, YEAH.
HOW YOU DOING, SIR?
I DIDN'T KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT KIND OF DIVE GEAR TO BRING,
SO I JUST BROUGHT
THE WHOLE THING.
IT'S PRETTY HEAVY.
WE'LL JUST SQUEEZE 'EM
UP IN THERE.
WHAT KIND OF
A BACKGROUND DO YOU HAVE?
WELL, I'VE DONE 13 YEARS
IN THE UNITED STATES
MARINE CORPS.
GOT OUT OF THAT,
WENT INTO COMMERCIAL DIVING,
DID THAT SINCE 2002.
YOU KNOW WHY I'M HERE,
RIGHT?
UH...
I DO DIVING.
YEAH, I UNDERSTOOD, UH,
TODD WAS SENDING
SOMEBODY UP TO, UH,
HE SAID "HELP US OUT."
I HOPE THAT'S THE CASE.
IT'S NOT JUST SOMETHING THAT
COME UP HERE TO, UH,
JUST KEEP AN EYE ON US,
'CAUSE, UH, WE KNOW
WHAT WE'RE DOING.
SENIOR HOFFMAN SENT ME
OUT HERE JUST TO --
JUST TO PROTECT
HIS INVESTMENT.
Fred: WE'RE AT CAMP.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT THIS, MAN?
I MEAN, THIS IS WOODS.
DEEP WOODS OUT HERE.
I'M MORE FOCUSED ON THAT,
UH, THAT CROSSING RIGHT THERE.
THAT'S IT.
THAT'S THE CABLE.
Narrator: TO GET TO THEIR CLAIM,
THE DAKOTA BOYS HAVE STRUNG
A 250-FOOT CABLE
ACROSS A CANYON
THAT'S 400 FEET DEEP.
THIS IS THE ONLY
WAY ACROSS, RIGHT?
WE HAVEN'T DROPPED ANYBODY.
YET.
CRAP.
Carlos:
I'M NOT SCARED OF HEIGHTS,
I'M JUST SCARED OF FALLING.
AND I'M SCARED OF
FALLING AND SURVIVING.
-Fred: ARE YOU READY?
-YEAH.
-ARE YOU READY?
-YEAH. I'M READY.
SON OF A [BLEEP].
[BLEEP] DAMN IT.
OH, [BLEEP]!
OH.
AH.
HO.
[ EXHALES ]
HOLY [BLEEP].
TOUCHDOWN. ALL RIGHT.
GOOD TO GO. ALL RIGHT.
TURN ME OFF.
AGH, [BLEEP] DAMN IT.
HE SEEMED A LITTLE
BIT NERVOUS ABOUT THAT.
I CAN UNDERSTAND THAT.
I DIDN'T HEAR HIM SCREAMING.
[ LAUGHS ]
THAT'S MY GEAR.
DON'T DROP.
DON'T DROP, PLEASE.
THIS IS JUST GETTING TO WORK,
THE COMMUTE TO WORK.
YEE-HAW!
I THOUGHT THEY JUST DO THIS
IN THIRD WORLD COUNTRIES
JUST TO GO TO WORK.
HOLY CRAP.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M HERE.
WELL, LET'S GRAB THAT BOX.
WE'VE GOT
A LONG WAY TO GO.
DO I HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
BEARS IN THIS KIND OF AREA?
A LITTLE BIT.
Narrator: THE MINE SITE IS
A GRUELING ONE-MILE HIKE
THROUGH McKINLEY'S
RUGGED CANYONS.
DOES THAT GO
ALL THE WAY AROUND?
DUSTIN, WES, AND PAUL HAVE
MINED TOGETHER FOR THREE YEARS.
LET'S DO THAT.
TODD'S MAN CARLOS
HAS NEVER MINED IN HIS LIFE.
STILL GOT THERE.
Fred: I WANT TO INTRODUCE YOU
TO CARLOS.
THIS IS PAUL.
HOW YOU DOING, PAUL?
HOW'S IT GOING, CARLOS?
WES.
HOW YOU DOING?
HELLO, WES, HOW YOU DOING?
AND DUSTIN.
HOW YOU DOING, DUSTIN?
NICE TO MEET YA.
WOO! I'M STILL OUT OF BREATH.
SO YOU BROUGHT US
SOME HELP, HUH?
WELL, TODD HOFFMAN
SENT HIM UP HERE
KIND OF TO KEEP AN EYE ON US.
I'M NOT HERE TO STEP
ON NOBODY'S TOES,
LOOK OVER YOUR SHOULDERS,
SO LET'S JUST CUT THAT OUT.
I'M JUST HERE
TO HELP YOU GUYS OUT.
LET 'EM KNOW WHAT KIND OF
QUALIFICATIONS YOU GOT.
UH, I'M A COMMERCIAL DIVER,
WORK OFFSHORE
ON OIL PLATFORMS,
BEEN DOING THAT
FOR ABOUT 15 YEARS NOW.
EVER BEEN IN ANYTHING
LIKE THIS?
YOU KNOW WHAT, I --
I THOUGHT I'VE BEEN
IN EVERY TYPE OF WATER
THERE IS,
BUT NO,
NOTHING LIKE THIS.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW ABOUT
THIS WHOLE TODD HOFFMAN THING.
Fred: NOT UP TO ME.
IT'S, UH --
I GUESS HE'S LOOKING
AFTER HIS INVESTMENT.
WHAT'D YOU GUYS SPEND
THE MONEY ON SO FAR?
RIGHT OFF,
WE GOT A DREDGE.
WE GOT HOT WATER SUITS,
YOU NAME IT.
EVERYTHING ASSOCIATED
WITH DIVING.
UH-HUH.
I'M STILL CURIOUS
WHAT THE HELL IS IN
THAT DAMN HEAVY BOX.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL SHOW YOU
MY BREAD 'N' BUTTER.
[ BLEEP ]
LOOK AT THAT.
WHAT I'M WORRIED ABOUT
IS IT GRABBING HOLD OF YOU AND
RIPPING YOUR DAMN HEAD OFF.
THAT THING'S NOT
COMING OFF MY HEAD.
NO, NO, IT'S NOT COMING.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT
YOUR HEAD RIPPING OFF.
[ LAUGHS ]
YOUR BODY.
WHAT WE'RE LOOKING
FOR IS SOMEBODY TO --
THAT'S AN ALL-AROUND PERSON
THAT CAN GET ALONG WITH US.
WE NEVER GO AWAY.
SO IF YOU DON'T
GET ALONG WITH US,
YOU CAN'T STAY HERE.
BUT IF YOU LIKE TO WORK,
YOU'RE GOING TO FIT RIGHT IN.
APPRECIATE IT, SENOR.
WELCOME ABOARD.
ALL RIGHT.
Dustin: I'M OPEN TO WORK
WITH ANYBODY THAT WORKS HARD.
I DON'T CARE WHERE THEY'RE
FROM OR WHAT THEY DO.
HE'S GOING TO HAVE TO DO
SOME GRUNT WORK
BEFORE HE'S EARNED
HIS RIGHT TO BE OUT HERE.
NONE OF THESE GUYS
TRUST ME RIGHT NOW,
AND AS FAR AS I DON'T EVEN
TRUST THESE GUYS.
I MEAN, THAT'S JUST --
THAT'S JUST COMMON SENSE.
THAT'S JUST HUMAN NATURE.
THESE GUYS CAN
THROW ME IN THE CREEK
IF THEY DON'T LIKE ME
AND THEY SAY,
"YEAH, CARLOS WHO?"
Dustin:
I DON'T CARE WHO SENT YOU.
THIS IS MY JOB SITE,
AND I'LL PUT YOU AWAY.
Narrator: UP AHEAD...
AND I'M [BLEEP] PISSED.
Carlos: [BLEEP] ME.
LOOK AT THAT [BLEEP], MAN.
THE RIVER IS PISSED TODAY,
BROTHER.
WE, UH, HOPE TO GET
THE DREDGE IN THE WATER TODAY
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
Narrator: HIGH IN
THE CHILKAT MOUNTAINS,
THE DAKOTA BOYS
ARE ON A TREASURE HUNT
FOR MILLIONS OF DOLLARS IN GOLD.
BEFORE THEY CAN GET
TO THE GOLD,
THEY HAVE TO EQUIP
THEIR REMOTE DIVE SITE
WITH ALL THE INFRASTRUCTURE
THEY NEED TO DREDGE.
FRED'S SPENT OVER $13,000
OF TODD'S $50,000 LOAN
ON THIS BRAND-NEW
SUCTION DREDGE.
IT'S A GOOD DAY.
VERY EXCITED BECAUSE
IT'S GOING TO PULL UP DIRT
AND GOLD SO
WE CAN GET RICH.
Narrator:
THE DREDGE IS A LIGHTWEIGHT
FLOATING WASH PLANT.
THE INTAKE HOSE SUCKS MATERIAL
FROM THE CREEK BED
AND WASHES IT THROUGH
AN ON-BOARD SLUICE BOX,
WHICH CATCHES THE HEAVY GOLD
IN ITS RIPPLES.
NOW WE KNOW WHERE IT GOES,
YOU CAN TAKE THAT OFF.
Fred: THAT DREDGE IS OUR MAIN
PIECE OF EQUIPMENT.
THAT WATER CAN COME UP,
JUST WASH EVERYTHING AWAY.
WE'VE HAD IT HAPPEN BEFORE.
SO WE HAVE TO BUILD
SOME KIND OF A SAFE HARBOR,
KEEP THE DIVER SAFE
AND GET OUT THERE
AND SERVICE THAT DREDGE.
AND THAT WILL STOP THAT CURRENT
FROM, UH, BEING DEADLY.
THE RIVER IS PISSED TODAY,
BROTHER.
TURN INTO A GOT-DANG MONSTER.
THIS WHITEWATER IS REALLY,
REALLY ROUGH.
WE NEED TO MAKE
SOME CALM WATER.
YEAH.
ALL THESE ROCKS HAVE TO LEAVE.
IT'S GOING TO BE
SOME BACK-BREAKING WORK.
AH, [BLEEP].
DON'T FALL IN.
Narrator: THE CREW HAS TO SHIFT
NINE TONS OF BOULDERS
TO BUILD A HARBOR
TO PROTECT THE DREDGE.
ROCKS RIGHT HERE, HUH?
I GUESS.
AND DON'T SMASH
YOUR [BLEEP] FINGERS.
HE GOT IT IN AND SAID,
"AH, I THOUGHT THIS WATER
WAS GOING TO BE COLD."
[ LAUGHTER ]
LIKE YOU SAID, MAN,
IT'S WORSE ON MY HANDS
THAN ON MY FEET, MAN.
Narrator: CARLOS IS USED TO
THE GULF OF MEXICO.
AT JUST 38 DEGREES,
THIS CREEK WATER
WILL CAUSE HYPOTHERMIA
IF THEY STAY IN TOO LONG.
Dustin: I'LL GET SOMEBODY
TO TURN ON
THE WATER HEATER SOON,
ALL RIGHT?
YEAH.
THAT'S SOME FUNNY STUFF
RIGHT THERE, MAN.
Fred: LOOKING GREAT.
LOOKING GREAT.
WE'RE GETTING CLOSER TO THE GOAL
EVERY TIME YOU TAKE A ROCK OUT.
WE'RE GETTING CLOSER TO IT.
ON THE TOP OF
THOSE OTHER ROCKS.
UP ON THE RIDGE,
YOUNGEST CREWMEMBER ZACK
IS HAULING LUMBER TO BUILD
THEIR DIVE PLATFORM.
I'M DOING THE BEST I CAN,
AND TO BE COMPLETELY HONEST,
WITHOUT ANY MORE PEOPLE,
THIS IS AS FAST AS IT GETS.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M HAPPY THEY
GAVE ME THIS JOB,
'CAUSE IT'S REALLY GOING TO
GIVE ME A GOOD IDEA
AS TO HOW MUCH THEY'RE
GOING TO RECOGNIZE THE WORK
THAT I CAN DO, 'CAUSE I CAN
TELL YOU RIGHT NOW --
NOT ONE OF THESE GUYS
CAN GET IT UP THERE
AS EFFICIENTLY AS ME.
I AIN'T GOING TO [BLEEP] WALK
THESE THINGS DOWN HERE SLOWLY.
LET 'EM FALL.
Dustin: HEY, ZACK,
YOU GOT A COPY, MAN?
YEAH, GO FOR ZACK.
WHAT'S TAKING YOU SO LONG,
MAN?
I'M JUST BUMPING
ALL THE BOARDS
DOWN TO THE BOTTOM
OF THE HILL AT ONE TIME
SO THAT I'M ONLY MAKING
ONE TRIP AND NOT 15.
WELL, WE NEED SOME
LUMBER OVER HERE, MAN.
YEAH, I'LL TAKE TWO
FROM MY PILE
AND GET 'EM OVER THERE
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE
AND COME BACK
AND FINISH THE JOB.
Dustin: DAMN KIDS THESE DAYS.
I HAVE TO STOP WHAT I'M DOING,
BUMPING ALL THESE BOARDS
DOWN THERE,
GO ALL THE WAY
TO WHERE THEY'RE AT,
SO THAT I CAN MOVE A BOARD
ONE BY ONE,
AND I'M [BLEEP] PISSED.
I GUESS I'M JUST USED TO PEOPLE
[BLEEP] DOING WHAT I WANT.
THERE HE IS.
HOW'S IT GOING?
[BLEEP] BULL [BLEEP].
IT'S KIND OF A SKETCHY TRAIL
TO HIKE AFTER YOU'VE BEEN
HIKING UP AND DOWN THAT [BLEEP]
HILL WITH THESE BOARDS.
JUST KEEP 'EM COMING,
MAN.
I NEED ABOUT A 30-INCH BOARD,
2x6, MAYBE.
Dustin: 30-INCH LONG,
2x6, PLEASE.
Fred: JUST TAKE A FEW MINUTES
AND I'LL GET IT DONE.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'VE GOT A DIVING BOARD!
Narrator: NEXT,
THEY NEED A SYSTEM
TO WINCH THEIR
1,000-POUND DREDGE
IN AND OUT OF
THE SAFE HARBOR.
Fred: UH, WELL, LET'S SEE.
CAN'T SLACK OFF.
I GOT IT. I GOT IT.
I TOTALLY GOT IT.
WE HOOK THAT WINCH RIGHT HERE
ON THIS POINT, RIGHT?
IT GOES UP TO THE BLOCK,
THROUGH THE BLOCK,
AND WE'RE ABLE TO PULL IT
ALL THE WAY OVER TO HERE.
IT'LL LIFT IT STRAIGHT UP.
I THINK THAT'S GOING TO WORK
RIGHT THERE.
YOU GUYS ARE ON
STEP SEVEN, MAN.
I'M STILL TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT YOU'RE TRYING TO DO.
Narrator: DUSTINGS PLAN,
SUSPEND 60 FEET OF CABLE
ACROSS THE CREEK AND INSTALL
A REMOTE CONTROL WINCH
THAT WILL HAUL THE DREDGE
UP AND OUT OF THE HARBOR
TO WHEREVER THEY NEED IT
FOR MINING.
I'M GOING TO SET
SOME ANCHOR POINTS.
WE'RE GOING TO RUN
A ROPE ACROSS,
AND WE'RE HOPEFULLY GOING TO
BE ABLE TO PICK THAT DREDGE
RIGHT OUT OF THE WATER.
I'VE GOT TO CLIMB UP
ALL THIS WET JUNK.
THERE'S ONLY
ONE WAY UP THIS,
AND HOPEFULLY I DON'T SLIDE OFF
INTO THE DAMN WATER
AND HURT MYSELF.
I'M ROPED IN,
BUT THAT'S JUST IN CASE I FALL.
IT SOUNDS ANGRY.
Narrator: THE FREEZING,
GLACIER-FED WATERS
OF McKINLEY SURGE THROUGH HERE
AT 129,000 GALLONS
EVERY MINUTE.
RIGHT NOW, IF DUSTIN WAS
TO SLIP AND FALL,
HE'S PRETTY MUCH
A STRAIGHT SHOT DOWN.
HE'D EITHER HIT THE LOG DECK,
WHICH WOULDN'T BE GOOD,
OR HE'D HIT THE WATER.
IT'D MESS HIM UP PRETTY BAD
WHERE HE'S AT NOW.
Dustin: JUST LIKE I THOUGHT,
SUPER SOFT [BLEEP] ROCK.
NOT SOLID?
[BLEEP] DAMN IT.
WHAT ABOUT RIGHT
ABOVE THAT SPOT?
[ GRUNTS ]
THERE IT GOES.
WOO!
HOLDING UP.
YOU CAN ONLY DO THAT
SO MANY TIMES
BEFORE YOUR LUCK
RUNS OUT, MAN.
YOU'RE MISTAKEN IF YOU THINK
THIS IS THE FIRST OR LAST TIME
THAT PAUL'S GOING TO HAVE
MY LIFE IN HIS HANDS.
Wes: I THINK HE'S GOT HIS ANCHOR
POINTS HOOKED UP OVER THERE.
WE'RE GOING TO TRY TO
GET A CABLE ACROSS NOW.
COMING UP.
YEP.
Dustin: IT LOOKS GOOD UP THERE.
I HOPE IT WORKS.
IT SHOULD.
WE GOT OUR CABLE UP OVER HERE.
WE'VE GOT OUR WINCH SET UP.
ALL WE'RE GOING TO DO
IS PUT 'EM TOGETHER
AND SEE IF THEY WORK.
Narrator: NOW,
THE MOMENT OF TRUTH --
WINCH THE $13,000 DREDGE
ACROSS THE RAGING CREEK
TO THEIR HARBOR
WITHOUT DESTROYING IT.
Fred: SO FAR IT'S OKAY.
HOLD IT.
YO, CARLOS!
GO GET THAT BLUE ROPE.
FOR WHAT?
SAFETY.
MAKE IT FAST!
Fred: GIVE IT PLENTY OF SLACK,
BUT I WANT YOU TO TIE IT
ONTO SOMETHING UP THERE.
I WANT YOU TO PICK UP
ON THE FRONT END.
YOU'RE NOT EVEN
LINED UP YET.
OH, PLEASE, YOU'RE GOING
TO [BLEEP] KILL ME!
DON'T MAKE ME TAKE CHARGE.
I DON'T WANT TO.
Fred: WHAT I WANT TO KNOW,
CAN YOU LIFT
THE FRONT OF THIS BARGE
WITH THAT ROPE AT ALL,
JUST THE WAY IT'S RIGGED?
I DIDN'T KNOW
WE WERE LIFTING IT.
I THOUGHT WE WERE
GUIDING IT IN.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE THIS OFF
THE DECK BEFORE YOU...
NO, YOU DON'T.
THAT'S HIGH.
THIS IS HIGH.
PULL ON IT,
THE [BLEEP] THING WILL COME
OFF OF THE GROUND.
I'M SORRY I'M CURSING AT YOU.
I'M TRYING TO CALM DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, DUSTIN.
WHAT IS THE PROBLEM?
I DON'T HAVE A PROBLEM.
TELL ME WHAT TO DO.
I ASKED YOU
A SIMPLE QUESTION.
NO, I CANNOT
LIFT IT UP.
NO, I CANNOT LIFT IT UP.
WHY DO YOU NEED TO
LIFT IT STRAIGHT UP?
BECAUSE WHEN THIS THING
SWINGS THIS WAY,
WHEN YOU PULL IT OUT,
IT'S GOING TO JUST
DESTROY THAT NOZZLE.
ALL YOU'VE GOT TO DO
IS HOLD YOUR HAND ON THERE
AND WALK WITH IT
JUST LIKE...
OH, REALLY?
GO AHEAD AND DO IT, THEN.
TURN IT THAT WAY.
I'M TURNING IT.
LIKE THAT.
IT'S GOING TO COME DOWN
ON YOUR HEAD, THAT ROPE.
JUST BE --
BE COOL, FRED.
OKAY.
WE'VE GOT IT.
IT'S CLEAR.
BE COOL.
OOP!
THIS [BLEEP] THING IS CAUGHT
IN THE ROPE. HOLD ON.
Narrator: A SNAG ON FRED'S
SAFETY ROPE IS
TIPPING THE DREDGE.
STOP.
STOP! ALL STOP!
IF THE FEROCIOUS
CURRENT CATCHES IT,
THEIR MINING SEASON
WILL BE OVER.
GET RID OF THAT [BLEEP] ROPE,
LET IT LOOSE!
LOOK OUT!
STOP! STOP!
IT'S CLEAR.
Narrator: THE DAKOTA BOYS
ARE STRUGGLING
TO GET THEIR GOLD-CATCHING
DREDGE TO THE SAFETY
OF THEIR ROCK HARBOR.
STOP! STOP!
ALL STOP!
BUT IT'S DANGEROUSLY SNAGGED.
STOP, STOP, STOP!
IT'S CAUGHT IN
THE [BLEEP] DAMN ROPE.
LET IT DOWN
AND I THINK WE GOT IT.
BE COOL, FRED.
YOU CAN'T HOLD IT?
LOOK AT THAT STUPID-ASS [BLEEP]
ROPE IS IN THE WAY.
CUT THAT MOTHER [BLEEP].
I GOT IT.
IT DIDN'T SWIVEL.
NOT TOO MUCH.
NOT TOO MUCH!
GOOD? WOO!
GOOD JOB, GUYS!
WOO!
IT WAS A LITTLE BIT IFFY
WHEN IT CAME OVER THE EDGE.
OTHER THAN THE FACT
WE WERE FRANTIC,
IT WENT SMOOTH.
Dustin: OVERALL,
IT'S BEEN A GREAT DAY.
WE GOT A LOT DONE.
OUR DREDGE IS OVER THE TOP
OF WHERE I'M ABOUT TO DREDGE.
THAT IS SUPER EXCITING.
WHAT'S GOING ON, ZACK?
WHAT'S UP, DUSTIN?
WHAT HAPPENED TODAY, MAN?
Narrator: ZACK HAS BEEN
HAULING DUSTIN'S LUMBER
TO THE DIVE SITE ALL DAY.
HE'S FINALLY GETTING
A BREAK AT CAMP.
YOU DOING OKAY
OUT HERE?
WELL, YOU TELL ME.
I'M DOING JUST FINE,
BUT HOW ABOUT A "THANKS, ZACK,"
OR A "GOOD JOB, ZACK,"
OR "YOU DID GOOD, I'M GLAD
YOU GOT THE BOARDS THERE"?
YOU DID A LOT OF WORK,
BUT YOU DIDN'T DO WHAT I ASKED.
FOR YOU TO PUT THAT ON ME,
THOUGH, IS A PROBLEM,
BECAUSE I DON'T FEEL
LIKE IT'S MY FAULT.
SO DO I HAVE TO BE
MORE SPECIFIC WITH YOU?
I FEEL LIKE WE NEED --
OUR COMMUNICATION
HAS TO BE PERFECT.
I AGREE, AND WHEN I SAY,
"I NEED BOARDS,"
YOU'RE BRINGING ME BOARDS.
WELL, THEY GOT TO YA,
DIDN'T THEY?
WELL...
LOOK, MAN, I'M USED TO
WORKING WITH MY GUYS.
THEY KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT I WANT WHEN I SAY IT.
WE SPEAK THE SAME LANGUAGE,
BUT I NEED YOU TO FIND
THAT AREA.
OKAY?
RIGHT.
IT'S JUST GOING TO TAKE
A LITTLE BIT OF TIME.
SOUNDS GOOD.
Narrator:
NEXT DAY IS THE FIRST DAY
OF DREDGING THE CREEK BED.
FRED'S EAGER TO PROVE
HIMSELF IN THE WATER.
HE'S A GOOD DIVER.
HE'S A GREAT DIVER, ACTUALLY.
AND HE WANTS TO SHOW US
WHAT HE'S MADE OF.
I THINK I'M BETTER TRAINED
AND MORE EXPERIENCED
TO HANDLE THIS SITUATION
THAN ANY ONE OF THE OTHERS.
Narrator:
LAST WEEK, DUSTIN FOUND PYRITE
DURING HIS TEST DRIVE.
KNOWN AS FOOL'S GOLD,
IT'S HEAVY AND OFTEN FOUND
ALONGSIDE GOLD.
NOW, AFTER WEEKS OF SETBACKS,
72-YEAR-OLD FRED
WILL DIVE WITH THE DREDGE
FOR THE FIRST TIME
TO HUNT FOR REAL GOLD.
IT'S JUST LIKE
RIDING A BICYCLE.
YOU DON'T EVER FORGET.
Narrator: 500 TONS
OF GLACIAL MELTWATER
POUR THROUGH THE CREEK
EVERY MINUTE.
FRED'S LIFE WILL DEPEND
ON HIS DIVER SUPPORT SYSTEM
WORKING PERFECTLY.
THE DAKOTA BOYS
HAVE ADAPTED THEIR DREDGE
WITH A PAIR OF ON-BOARD
WATER HEATERS
AND AIR COMPRESSORS.
THE SYSTEM FEEDS WARM WATER
INTO THE DIVER'S WET SUIT
AND VITAL AIR TO HIS MASK.
THEIR SET-UP IS NEW
AND COMPLETELY UNTESTED.
I AIN'T NEVER SEEN
A HONDA
THAT WON'T [BLEEP] START
AND KEEP RUNNING,
AND THIS ONE WON'T EVEN
TRY TO [BLEEP] FIRE OFF.
I DON'T REALLY KNOW WHAT IN
THE WORLD'S GOING ON DOWN THERE.
APPARENTLY THEY'VE
HAVING SOME PROBLEMS
PRIMING A PUMP
OR SOMETHING.
[ ENGINE STARTS ]
NOTHING'S TOTALLY PLANNED.
THERE'S NOT A CHECK LIST
GOING ON.
WHY WON'T THE THING
KEEP A PRIME?
I DON'T KNOW.
Narrator: CARLOS' 13 YEARS
AS A COMMERCIAL DIVER
COMBINED WITH HIS TIME
AS A MARINE
MEAN HE'S USED TO
RIGOROUS SAFETY
AND STRICT DIVING PROTOCOLS.
AS FAR AS GIVING ME CONFIDENCE
OF GETTING IN THE WATER,
NOT UNTIL ALL THESE BUGS
ARE WORKED OUT.
Paul: I'M NOT SURE
WHAT WENT ON THERE.
I'VE NEVER HAD A ENGINE
THAT HARD TO START.
MAYBE 'CAUSE IT WAS BRAND-NEW,
NEVER BEEN RUN BEFORE.
I JUST FOUND OUT THAT HOT WATER
MACHINE IS ON THE DREDGE, RIGHT?
YEAH.
SO YOU GOT
THE HOT WATER MACHINE
ON THE DREDGE,
GOT YOUR VOL INTAKE,
YOUR AIR ON THE DREDGE.
YEAH.
SO IF THAT AIR GOES,
THAT AIR COMES OUT
OR SOMETHING HAPPENS
WITH THE AIR COMPRESSOR,
HOW MUCH VOLUME
DO YOU GOT TO BREATH?
ABOUT TWO
TO THREE BREATHES.
THE COWBOY ATTITUDE
THAT THEY HAVE HERE...
I JUST HOPE IT
KEEPS GOING THEIR WAY.
Fred:
I NEED A CARABINER OR SOMETHING
TO HOOK THAT SAFETY LINE
TO THIS THING IN THE BACK.
Narrator:
FRED STRAPS ON 60 POUNDS
OF LEAD TO STOP McKINLEY'S
LETHAL CURRENTS
DRAGGING HIM DOWNSTREAM.
THAT'S JUST FOR
THE CARABINER, YEAH.
WE HAVE...
ABOUT TO GET A RADIO CHECK.
Dustin:
YOU SHOULD BE GETTING SOME GOOD,
WARM WATER RIGHT NOW.
NO, I DON'T THINK YOU'RE
GOING TO GET CONSISTENT
OUT OF THIS [BLEEP].
YOU READY TO GO?
YEAH?
YEAH.
OKAY.
EVERYTHING'S GOOD.
WE'RE GOING THIS WAY.
Dustin: ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE GOING TO GIVE YOU
A QUICK COUNTDOWN.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
GET IT, FRED.
Narrator: UP AHEAD...
Dustin: THERE IS NOWHERE
WHERE THE GOLD IS SITTING
ON THE SURFACE RIGHT NOW.
WE JUST FOUND IT.
Dustin: THREE, TWO, ONE.
GET IT, FRED.
Narrator: DESPERATE TO FIND GOLD
AT THEIR MINE SITE,
72-YEAR-OLD FRED HURT
DREDGES THE DEADLY RAPIDS
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
I KNOW IT'S NOT YOU PULLING.
THE CURRENT'S TRYING
TO DRAG HIM.
IT FEELS LIKE HE'S TRYING
TO GET AWAY FROM ME.
Dustin: WELL, YOU DO THAT.
HE WANTS IT OUT THERE.
PUSH IT OUT THERE.
Narrator: FRED USES
THE SIX-INCH INTAKE HOSE
TO SUCK MATERIAL UP
FROM THE CREEK BED
ONTO THE FLOATING DREDGE.
THE ONBOARD SLUICE BOX
WASHES THE GRAVEL,
CATCHING THE HEAVY GOLD
IN ITS RIFFLES.
RIGHT NOW, LOOKS LIKE HE'S
DOING PRETTY GOOD DOWN THERE.
I SEE A LOT OF BLACK MATERIAL
COMING OUT OF THE BACK OF IT.
YEAH, FRED,
YOU'RE DREDGING AGAIN, MAN.
WOO.
Dustin: ABOUT DAMN TIME.
UNDERWATER, DIGGING DIRT.
Dustin: DON'T GO INTO
THAT [BLEEP] WHITEWATER.
THE WATER'S COMING UP RIGHT NOW.
DON'T GO FOR THE GLORY.
GO FOR SAFETY RIGHT NOW.
Dustin: HEY, FRED,
IT SOUNDS LIKE YOUR VENT
ON YOUR SIDE OPENED UP.
OKAY, YOU DON'T
HAVE ANY AIR?
AH, [BLEEP].
HEY, HE'S GOT NO AIR!
HEY, LET'S JUST GET HIM
OUT OF THE WATER RIGHT NOW.
LET'S JUST FIGURE OUT
WHAT'S GOING ON.
ALL RIGHT,
THE VALVE'S STUCK OPEN.
BRINGING HIM IN.
WATCH HIS HEAD.
Dustin: WATCH YOUR HEAD, FRED.
WATCH YOUR HEAD.
OH, IT IS GOOD TO GET AIR.
BOY, WHEN YOU JUST DON'T
QUITE HAVE ENOUGH AIR
COMING INTO THAT MASK.
SOMETHING -- SOMETHING'S
GOING ON WITH THAT MASK.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
GOING ON WITH IT.
WE MIGHT HAVE
SOME OF THE SILT
BUILT UP IN THE REGULATOR
OR SOMETHING.
Dustin: HOW YOU DOING?
TAKE THE TOP OFF?
OKAY.
Carlos: IF TODD HOFFMAN
WERE TO WALK AROUND
THAT CORNER RIGHT NOW
AND SEE WHAT THE HECK
WAS GOING ON,
I DON'T THINK THAT HE WOULD BE
REALLY HAPPY AT ALL.
Dustin: MECHANICAL PROBLEM
WITH YOUR AIR FLOW,
THAT IS THE LAST THING
YOU WANT HAPPENING
WHEN YOU'RE DOWN THERE.
YOU COULD DEAL WITH GETTING COLD
AND BEING PISSED OFF.
LET ME CATCH MY BREATH.
GOING WITHOUT AIR
IS PRETTY HARD FOR ANYBODY.
Carlos: THIS IS NOT
A GOT-DANG PLAYGROUND.
THIS IS --
THIS IS SCARY STUFF.
COME OVER THERE, FRED.
SENOR FRED, MAN,
HIS LIFE MEANS SOMETHING.
EVEN, YOU KNOW,
I JUST MET THE GUY.
HIS LIFE MEANS
SOMETHING TO ME.
IT WAS A COMPLETE
[BLEEP]-SHOW TODAY.
COMPLETE [BLEEP]-SHOW.
I DON'T THINK THIS FRICKING
AIR COMPRESSOR'S
PUSHING TOO MUCH.
Narrator:
DIVE EXPERT CARLOS CHECKS
FRED'S MASK FOR FAULTS.
[ COUGHS, SPITS ]
YEAH, IT'S NOT PUSHING
ENOUGH AIR FOR THIS, FRED.
YEAH?
IT'S NOT PUSHING
ENOUGH AIR FOR THIS.
YOU'RE KIDDING.
THIS IS FOR OUR MAIN
AIR RIGHT HERE.
IT JUST WON'T --
UNLESS YOUR BLOCK.
THAT'S THE ONLY THING
I CAN THINK OF.
OR IT'S JUST NOT
ENOUGH PRESSURE.
HAD TO BUY IT SIGHT UNSEEN
WHEN I GOT THERE,
SO I DIDN'T HAVE ANY CHANCE
TO REALLY CHECK IT OUT.
I WON'T TAKE MUCH
TO GET IT WORKING.
WE'LL FIGURE IT OUT.
THAT'S WHAT WE ALWAYS DO.
WE FIX THE STUFF
THAT GOES WRONG
AND WE KEEP GOING ALONG
AND KEEP PLUGGING ALONG.
JUST NEVER SEEN THINGS
DONE THIS WAY.
Narrator:
FRED ABANDONED HIS DIVE
WHEN HE RAN OUT OF AIR,
BUT HE STILL SUCKED UP
ENOUGH SURFACE MATERIAL
FROM THE CREEK BED
FOR A SMALL TEST PAN.
YOU AIN'T NEVER SEEN PANNING.
NOPE, ONLY ON TV.
IT'S A NEW THING, MAN.
ONLY IN THE MOVIES.
FIRST THING YOU NEED
TO DO WITH THE THING,
YOU JUST PUT WATER
IN YOUR PAN.
RIGHT.
AND WHAT YOU WANT TO DO,
DRAW YOU A CIRCLE,
KIND OF LIKE THAT.
IF THERE'S ANY GOLD IN THERE,
IT WILL SINK TO THE BOTTOM,
AND WE'RE GOING TO HOPE
FOR THE BEST.
NICE AND SLOW.
TILT IT TO THE FRONT
A LITTLE BIT.
UH-OH. UH-OH.
THERE'S SOMETHING
DOWN THERE.
I SEE SOMETHING.
I DID TOO.
UH-OH.
HOLY [BLEEP].
WOO!
WE GOT YOU
A LITTLE GOLD IN THERE.
THAT'S WHAT
WE'RE LOOKING FOR.
THAT'S NEAT.
HOLY [BLEEP].
WOO!
OH, LOOK AT ALL THAT
SMALL GOLD THAT'S IN THERE.
HOW DEEP DID YOU GET,
A FOOT?
RIGHT OFF THE SURFACE.
WE ARE GOING TO DO GREAT.
YEP. LOOK AT THAT [BLEEP].
NO, NO, THAT'S REAL GOOD.
I TOLD YOU.
"I TOLD YOU."
I TOLD YOU,
[BLEEP] DAMN IT.
FOR SOME REASON,
I'M NOT GETTING EXCITED
AS MUCH AS YOU GUYS.
I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW.
Wes: YOU SEE SOME OF
THE PLACES WE DUG, CARLOS,
WE DUG ALL DAY LONG AND DIDN'T
COME UP WITH THAT MUCH GOLD.
Dustin: YOU DON'T
UNDERSTAND THIS,
BUT YOU DON'T FIND
GOLD ON THE SURFACE.
SITTING ON THE SURFACE.
NO.
IN THE TOP OF A FOOT OF DIRT.
THERE IS NOWHERE
WHERE THE GOLD IS SITTING
ON THE SURFACE RIGHT NOW.
WE JUST FOUND IT.
THAT'S GOLD.
Fred: IT PUMPED
EVERYBODY UP.
THEY REALIZED THE SIGNIFICANCE
OF JUST THOSE 10 OR 15
LITTLE PIECES OF GOLD IN THAT.
Dustin: HELL YEAH.
IT FEELS DAMN GOOD.
INCREDIBLE.
WE FOUND GOLD!
Narrator: UP AHEAD...
ALL RIGHT, THEN I'M GONE.
THEN I'LL LEAVE.
THEN BE GONE.
[ BLEEP ]
IT'S THAT
[BLEEP] SIMPLE.
I'M OUT OF HERE.
WE'D HAVE BEEN
DOING REALLY GOOD.
Dustin: THAT'S ONLY
THE INSPECTION MAT.
IT'S GOLD.
SO WE'VE GOT THAT GOLD
SPREAD ALL THE WAY THROUGH
THAT WHOLE SLUICE.
THAT'S GOT-DANG GOOD NEWS,
YOU KNOW?
Narrator: IN THEIR SEARCH
FOR A HUGE DEPOSIT OF GOLD,
THE DAKOTA BOYS HAVE FOUND
THEIR FIRST FLAKES.
CARLOS, WE'RE GOING TO TURN YOU
FROM A DIVER TO A GOLD MINER.
I -- I DO NOT WANT TO CATCH
THIS KIND OF FEVER.
OH, YOU'RE GOING TO
CATCH IT.
THERE AIN'T NO WAY
YOU CAN MISS IT.
THEN YOU'RE
GOING TO CURSE US.
Dustin:
A PEANUT BUTTER JAR OF THAT
STUFF WILL BUY YOU A HOUSE.
NO [BLEEP].
CASH MONEY.
ONE LITTLE JAR, HUH?
THAT JAR OF GOLD
THAT CAN BUY A HOUSE
IS ONLY GOOD IF YOU'RE
AROUND TO SPEND IT.
IT AIN'T YOUR AVERAGE,
UH, AREA TO GO VISIT, IS IT?
I WOULD NEVER EXPECT US
TO HAVE A DIVING GIG OUT HERE
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE FOREST.
[ LAUGHTER ]
Narrator: AT BASE CAMP, JEN,
ZACK'S MOM
AND FRED'S GIRLFRIEND,
HAS JOINED THE CREW TO CELEBRATE
A SUCCESSFUL END
TO A TOUGH WEEK.
YOU WANT A BEER
OR SOMETHING, CARLOS?
NO, I'M GOOD TO GO.
I DO APPRECIATE IT, THOUGH.
WELL, GUYS, I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT YOU GUYS,
BUT I THINK CARLOS
EARNED HIS WAY
A LITTLE BIT
INTO THE GROUP.
HEY, WHAT THE HELL
IS THIS [BLEEP]?
FRED,
I BEEN HERE FOR A MONTH
AND I HAVEN'T EARNED MY WAY
INTO THE GROUP YET.
ALL THE SUDDEN, HE COMES IN FOR
ONE DAY AND HE'S [BLEEP] IN.
WHAT IS THIS [BLEEP],
FRED?
I'M STILL FIGHTING
TO GET MY [BLEEP]
RESPECT OUT OF
THIS CREW HERE.
WELL, YOU KNOW, YOU'RE JUST
A LITTLE WHIPPERSNAPPER.
WHAT THE [BLEEP] ARE YOU GUYS
SINGLING ME OUT FOR?
THIS IS COMPLETE BULL [BLEEP].
YOU'RE THE YOUNGEST, MAN.
THIS IS [BLEEP] UP.
HE'S THE LOW MAN ON
THE TOTEM POLE NOW, NOT ME.
YEAH, BUT I GOT EXPERIENCE.
I GOT TONS.
I GOT TONS EXPERIENCE.
AND I DON'T GOT
NO EXPERIENCE.
I BEEN WORKING AT A DOLLAR TREE
MY WHOLE LIFE, RIGHT?
SOMEWHERE AROUND 40,
YOU'LL FIGURE OUT
HOW STUPID YOU WERE AT 24.
[ LAUGHS ]
'CAUSE SOMEWHERE
AROUND 21,
I WAS THE SMARTEST SON
OF A [BLEEP] ON EARTH.
GOD, I WAS STUPID.
Jen: PROBLEM IS,
HE HAS THE EXPERIENCE
TO BACK UP SOME OF THE STUFF
THAT COMES OUT OF HIS MOUTH.
HE'S STILL YOUNG.
HE'S STILL YOUNG,
BUT HE DOES HAVE SOME...
THE IDEALS OF
A YOUNG PERSON,
HIS OPTIMISM IS JUST LIKE
A YOUNG PERSON.
IT'S -- HE'S GOT ALL THESE HUGE,
COMPLICATED THINGS...
DUSTIN, I -- [BLEEP] I
ACCOMPLISHED MORE THINGS
THAN YOU HAVE
ANY [BLEEP] IDEA.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT THE [BLEEP]
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
YOU DON'T KNOW ME
BECAUSE YOU'VE ONLY BEEN HERE
FOR A MONTH WITH ME.
YOU DON'T HAVE ANY [BLEEP] IDEA
OF WHAT I'VE BEEN THROUGH...
I KNOW THAT YOU TALK LIKE --
AND WHAT I'VE DONE
AND THE EXPERIENCE
THAT I [BLEEP] HAVE
AND WHAT I'VE SACRIFICED
TO GET TO THIS POINT
TO BE QUALIFIED
TO BE HERE IN THIS [BLEEP] CREW
WITH YOU GUYS.
FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
YOU'RE NOT QUALIFIED
TO BE IN THIS [BLEEP] CREW.
YOU'RE QUALIFIED TO --
ALL RIGHT. THEN I'M GONE.
THEN I'LL LEAVE.
THEN BE GONE.
IT'S THAT [BLEEP] SIMPLE.
I'M OUT OF HERE.
GO. DO YOUR THING.
THAT [BLEEP] SIMPLE.
[BLEEP].
WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT?
ZACK, IS THIS FOR REAL?
THIS IS [BLEEP] FOR REAL,
AND I DON'T [BLEEP]
NEED YOU IN HERE.
I'M OUT OF HERE.
FRED, LET IT GO. FRED.
OH, HOLD ON, NOW. HOLD UP.
FRED.
DUSTIN WOULD GET HIS ASS
TIED UP IN A LITTLE KNOT
AND PUT ON THE [BLEEP] CHOKER
AND SENT BACK UP THE HILL
WITHIN THE FIRST HOUR
OF BEING ON
THE RIGGING CREWS
THAT I GREW UP WITH.
WHAT'S UP, DUDE?
LITTLE BIT OF LIGHTHEARTED
BULL [BLEEP].
OH, COME ON!
FIRST OF ALL, WE WERE
JUST KIDDING, THE FIRST THING.
I CAN TELL YOU THAT
RIGHT NOW.
JUST GOT TO LEARN
HOW TO DEAL WITH IT.
I MEAN, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO GET UPSET ABOUT IT.
I'VE LEARNED HOW TO DEAL
WITH IT, FRED.
WELL, THEN OBVIOUSLY NOT.
THERE'S A FINE LINE
BETWEEN MAKING JOKES,
MESSING WITH THE NEW GUY,
MESSING WITH THE GREENHORN,
AND NOT
RESPECTING SOMEBODY.
SORRY 'BOUT YOUR SON.
ARE YOU?
IS THAT WHY YOU
CAN'T LOOK AT ME?
TOLD YOU THIS [BLEEP]
WOULD GET WEIRD.
Fred: TELL YOU ONE THING
WE DON'T DO IS QUIT,
'CAUSE WE GOT
WHAT IT TAKES!
I DON'T CARE
WHERE YOU WERE.
YOU GOT 20 GUYS OUT THERE,
AND DURING BREAK TIME,
THEY'RE ALL JUMPING YOUR ASS
'CAUSE THEY DON'T LIKE, UH,
YOU'RE TOO [BLEEP] TALL.
YOU'RE TOO SKINNY.
YOU'RE TOO FAT.
I HAVE [BLEEP] BEEN PICKED
ON ALL MY [BLEEP] LIFE.
LOOK AT THAT BOOT,
DOWN THERE.
YOU KNOW,
PEOPLE DO THAT.
PEOPLE ARE NOT KIND.
YOU JUST HAVE
TO DEAL WITH IT.
IT'S LIFE.
DUSTIN OBVIOUSLY DOESN'T
KNOW THE WORD "TACT."
Dustin:
HOW'S THIS FOR TACT, FRED?
I'M DONE WITH THIS
[BLEEP] ANYWAY, SO...
Fred:
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
NO, I'M [BLEEP]
WORRIED ABOUT IT.
WELL, IT'S UP TO HIM.
YEAH, NO.
IT'S NOT UP TO HIM ANYMORE.
GET YOUR [BLEEP].
GET THE [BLEEP]
OUT OF HERE, MAN.
YEAH, THAT'S DEFINITELY
I WANT TO STAY HERE
FOR THAT [BLEEP]
BULL [BLEEP], YEAH.
THANKS FOR YOUR ADVICE, FRED,
BUT I'M [BLEEP] OUT OF HERE.
I HAVE A MAJOR AMOUNT
OF RESPECT FOR FRED,
I ALWAYS WILL,
WHICH I DO NOT HAVE FOR DUSTIN.
Dustin: I'D HAVE FIRED HIM
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
BUT I TRIED TO
GIVE HIM A CHANCE
JUST BECAUSE OF
HIS CONNECTION WITH FRED.
OH, THE NEW GUY COMES IN
AND I'M STILL THE [BLEEP]...
YEAH. [BLEEP] THAT.
HE'S DONE.
HE DOESN'T NEED
TO WORK HERE ANYMORE.
HE NEEDS TO GO LOGGING.
HERE WE GO.
Narrator: ON THE NEXT EPISODE...
WOO-HOO!
THIS IS CRAZY!
I'M TRYING TO PREVENT A PROBLEM
BEFORE IT HAPPENS, THAT'S ALL.
AAAH! STOP!
THERE IT GOES.
WHOA!
I'LL BE DAMNED.
THERE'S A LITTLE
NUGGET IN THERE.
WOO-HOO-HOO!
WE ARE GOING TO BE RICH.
CLEAN THAT SUCKER OUT!
WAY TO GO, BUDDY!
CLEAN IT OUT.
GOOD JOB.
IT'S ONLY GOING TO GET BIGGER.
IT'S ONLY GOING TO
GET BIGGER.
WE GOT SOME GOLD.