YES,
THAT'S WHAT I'M GONNA DO.
IF ANYONE'S GONNA DIE HERE,
THIS IS HOW THEY'RE GONNA DIE.
THIS IS CRAZY.
Paul: CARLOS HAS THE LOOK
OF FEAR IN HIS EYES.
DON'T SNAP ON ME, PLEASE.
**
GET THAT DAMN THING
OFF YOUR BACK.
[ LAUGHS ]
PUT YOUR [BLEEP]
**
Carlos: AH [BLEEP]
Dustin: CARLOS.
**
IS THERE GOLD
ON THIS CREEK OR NOT?
THIS IS SOME OF
THE HARDEST [BLEEP]
TO GET TO ON THE EARTH.
THIS COULD BE THE MOMENT.
**
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
DISCOVERY COMMUNICATIONS
**
I'LL GO DOWN, AND I'MA TAKE UP
SOME SERIOUS YARDAGE.
DUSTIN'S A BEAST, MAN.
HE'D PROBABLY BE THERE
ALL FRICKING DAY, MAN.
Narrator:
IN REMOTE McKINLEY CREEK,
DUSTIN HURT IS RISKING
HIS LIFE SEARCHING
FOR A POCKET OF GOLD
THAT WILL MAKE HIM
AND HIS CREW RICH.
I, UH, KNOCKED
THIS OUT PRETTY GOOD.
GONNA BE FUN.
**
AIR'S GOOD.
WATER'S GOOD.
**
WHOO-HOO.
YEAH! [ LAUGHS ]
Narrator: THE DAKOTA BOYS
HAVE SO FAR DREDGED
A HALF OUNCE OF GOLD
WORTH ONLY $600.
BUT THAT GOLD IS A SIGN
THAT THEY COULD BE
JUST FEET
FROM FINDING MILLIONS
ON THE BEDROCK
BENEATH THESE RAPIDS.
HOW YOU DOING THERE,
DUSTIN?
Dustin:
* I'M SWIMMING AGAIN
* DUSTIN SWIMMING AGAIN
* DIGGING AGAIN
* NA, NA, NA, NA, NA
Narrator: LAST WEEK,
THEY BUILT A DIVERSION
TO SHIELD THEMSELVES FROM
THE 120,000 GALLONS OF WATER
THAT COME CRASHING DOWN
EVERY MINUTE.
ALL RIGHT.
GIVE IT HELL.
Wes: HEY, WHAT'S THAT?
**
HEY.
WE GOT A HELICOPTER.
WHAT THE HELL?
MAN, SOMEBODY'S DEFINITELY
CHECKING US OUT NOW.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THE HELL IT IS.
MUST BE SOME GOVERNMENT AGENCY
OR SOMETHING.
HEY. YOU -- YOU THINK
MSHA WOULD DO THAT?
THEY COULD DO JUST ABOUT
WHATEVER THEY WANT TO.
HEY, IT LOOKS LIKE
THEY'RE LANDING.
MAN, IT LOOKS LIKE
THEY ARE.
THEY'RE SETTING DOWN
OVER THERE.
LOOK, UH, YOU GOT
ENOUGH PEOPLE HERE.
I'M GONNA GO AHEAD AND, UH,
PASS YOU OFF TO CARLOS.
AND, UH,
I'M GONNA GO OVER THERE
AND SEE WHAT
THE HELL'S GOING ON.
**
-[ BLEEP ]
-MORNING, FRED.
WHAT THE HELL
YOU DOING OUT HERE?
WELL, YOU REMEMBER HUDSON.
-HUDSON? YEAH. THE LITTLE KID.
-YEP.
WE, UH, WE HAD
A LITTLE BUSINESS UP HERE.
I THOUGHT WE'D SWING BY
AND SEE HOW YOU GUYS ARE DOING,
HOPEFULLY PICK UP SOME GOLD.
Narrator: SIX WEEKS AGO,
FRED TOOK A LOAN
FROM TODD HOFFMAN
TO FUND THEIR SEASON.
I WILL BE CHECKING IN.
THE DAKOTA BOYS
NEED TO REPAY THAT $50,000
BEFORE THEY MAKE
A DIME IN PROFIT.
THIS IS LIKE "JURASSIC PARK"
OR SOMETHING, FRED.
TO PROTECT HIS INVESTMENT,
TODD SENT IN CARLOS
AS HIS MAN ON THE CREW.
DUSTIN.
YEAH, MAN.
PUT A GAME FACE ON, BROTHER.
WE GOT GUESTS
ON THE PREMISES.
TODD HOFFMAN IS
PAYING US A VISIT.
-HOLY CRAP.
-AND THAT, GENTLEMEN,
IS OUR OPERATION
RIGHT THERE.
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
IT LOOKS LIKE, UH,
FRED IS GIVING TODD HOFFMAN
ALL THE SKINNY
WHAT'S GOING AROUND HERE.
WE'VE GOT A PLUNGE POOL
OUT THERE.
WE GOT BIG ROUND ROCKS.
AND IT'S ON THE INSIDE
BEND OF A RIVER.
THERE'S GOLD IN THAT,
A LOT OF GOLD.
AND HOW DO YOU
GET OVER THERE?
YOU GOT --
WELL, WE GOT --
WE GOT TO GO ACROSS THESE...
-YOU GOTTA WALK ON THEM PLANKS?
THAT'S A WALKWAY?
-YEAH, THAT'S A WALKWAY.
READY?
NO, I'M NOT READY.
BUT LET'S GO.
**
THOSE BOARDS DON'T LOOK
LIKE THEY GONNA HOLD ME.
HOW -- HOW MUCH
WEIGHT WILL IT HOLD?
TODD, I AM NOT SURE.
I NEVER CHECKED IT.
300-POUND GUY
GOING ACROSS
THAT [BLEEP] WALKWAY.
PANTS ARE FALLING DOWN.
Carlos: ALL RIGHT. HERE COMES
THE ENTERTAINMENT.
THEY'RE GONNA TRY TO ATTEMPT
TO CROSS THIS BRIDGE.
GOOD LORD.
HEY. IF YOU DIE,
DO I HAVE TO PAY YOU BACK?
FRED!
GET OFF THAT ONE.
HEY, YOU MIGHT HAVE
TO LEAN OUT A LITTLE BIT.
I DON'T WANNA PUT
TWO PEOPLE ON THAT.
YOU MIGHT HAVE TO LEAN OUT
A LITTLE BIT HERE.
I GUARANTEE YOU,
I'M THE ONLY 300-POUNDER
THAT'S DOING THIS
RIGHT NOW.
**
TODD HOFFMAN MADE IT
ACROSS THE BRIDGE
WITHOUT KILLING HIMSELF.
YOU WANT -- YOU WANT TO
TAKE A BREATHER HERE?
CARLOS.
HOW YOU DOING?
[ SPEAKS SPANISH ]
YEAH, MAN.
**
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE,
MAN?
I CAME TO SEE WHAT
THE HELL'S GOING ON.
THE ONLY INFORMATION
I'M GETTING IS FROM CARLOS.
YOU JUST FLEW INTO MY --
FLEW INTO MY CLAIM.
FLEW INTO YOUR CLAIM,
MAN.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO START
FLYING INTO YOUR CLAIM.
**
Todd: HOLY [BLEEP]
TELL ME THE TRUTH, MAN.
WHAT THE HELL --
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
UP HERE?
I'M CHECKING ON
THAT 50 GRAND
IT'S A LOT OF MONEY.
I GOTTA -- I GOTTA ASK.
HOW MUCH GOLD YOU GUYS GOT?
I WANNA SEE IT.
-SHOW ME THAT NUGGET.
HERE'S IS WHAT WE GOT
RIGHT HERE, GUYS.
HERE'S OUR NUGGET AND THE REST
OF EVERYTHING ELSE
THAT WE'VE GOT SO FAR.
OKAY. ONE NUGGET.
A HALF OUNCE.
YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN DREDGING
FOR PROBABLY A WEEK OR TWO.
WHAT DO YOU REALLY THINK
THAT'S TELLING YOU? BE HONEST.
WE'RE LOOKING
FOR A POCKET, MAN.
WE'RE LOOKING FOR THAT
ONE LITTLE POCKET.
I DON'T KNOW HOW BIG
THAT POCKET'S GONNA BE.
BUT IT'S ON THIS CREEK.
Paul: WE FIND
A COFFEE-CAN-SIZED POCKET,
AND WE'VE GOT IT.
ALL IT TAKES
IS JUST ONE STRIKE.
YEAH, THAT COULD BE
$4 MILLION WORTH OF GOLD
IN THAT ONE LITTLE POCKET
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
BE HONEST. BE HONEST.
LISTEN, NO BS.
WE HAVEN'T GOTTEN TO IT YET
BECAUSE THIS IS SOME
OF THE HARDEST [BLEEP]
TO GET TO ON THE EARTH.
IS THERE GOLD HERE,
OR IS THIS BS?
-YEAH, THERE'S GOLD.
-ARE YOU TELLING ME
THAT I JUST LOST MY MONEY,
OR ARE YOU TELLING ME
THAT YOU FRICKING GUYS
ARE GONNA COME OUT OF HERE
WITH SOME DAMN GOLD?
WE'RE GONNA COME OUT WITH GOLD.
I JUST HAVEN'T GOTTEN IT YET.
YOU'RE IN CHARGE.
I GAVE YOU 50,000 BUCKS.
NOBODY HERE IS MY BOSS.
I NEED TO MAKE THAT
VERY CLEAR.
-IS THIS TRUE, FRED?
-WELL, THAT'S TRUE.
'CAUSE I THOUGHT
YOU WERE IN CHARGE, FRED,
IF YOU WANNA KNOW THE TRUTH.
-WELL...
-I GAVE YOU THAT MONEY.
YOU'RE IN CHARGE.
THIS IS MY GOLD.
Narrator: EVEN THOUGH FRED
AND THE TEXANS
HAVE A SHARE OF THE GOLD,
DUSTIN OWNS THIS CLAIM.
IT LOOKS LIKE HE'S GOT
A BIG HEAD RIGHT NOW.
YOU AND I HAVE MINED
LONGER THAN DUSTIN.
NO OFFENSE TO DUSTIN,
BUT WE'VE GOTTEN
OUR ASS KICKED BEFORE,
AND A HALF OUNCE
AIN'T GONNA PAY THE BILLS.
-THAT'S RIGHT.
-RIGHT?
-I -- I UNDERSTAND.
-SO I SUGGEST YOU AND ME
GO COME UP WITH A PLAN B,
GET IN THAT DAMN HELICOPTER.
THAT'S THE MOST
LOGICAL THING TO DO.
BETWEEN ME AND YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
NOT DUSTIN.
-LET'S GO.
**
HEY. CARLOS.
SEE YA, GUYS. GOOD LUCK.
**
Dustin: IT'S GONNA BE BEAUTIFUL.
WE'RE GONNA BE RICH.
I'LL GET HIM HIS GOLD
AND HIS 50 GRAND BACK,
AND THEY CAN GO AWAY.
SEE YOU LATER.
I'M GONNA HOLD YOU
TO THAT 20 OUNCES THOUGH.
YOU HEAR ME?
SEE YOU LATER, FRED.
ALL RIGHT.
Narrator: UP AHEAD...
AH [BLEEP]
[ GROANS ]
Dustin: CARLOS!
**
Dustin: UM, ALL RIGHT.
FOR THIS WEEK,
UH,
WE'RE GONNA KEEP DIGGING.
LET'S JUST NOT STOP DIGGING.
WE'RE JUST GONNA HIT BEDROCK,
UH...
FELLOWS, THERE'S SOMETHING
THAT I HADN'T TOLD YOU.
BUT, UH, LOOK, UH,
TODD'S BEEN
PUTTING THE SCREWS ON US.
YOU SAW US FLY
UP THE CREEK.
WE WERE, UH,
LOOKING AT PLAN B.
**
WE DON'T PRODUCE IN
THE NEXT COUPLE OF WEEKS
AT LEAST 20 OUNCES OF GOLD,
HE WANTS US TO MOVE ON,
HAVE PLAN B,
MOVE SOMEWHERE ELSE.
I DON'T CARE WHAT TODD SAYS.
WE'RE NOT GOING SOMEWHERE ELSE
AND DIGGING.
IT'S NOT HAPPENING.
-WE'RE SO CLOSE
TO GETTING TO THE BOTTOM.
I THINK WE SHOULD JUST
KEEP RIGHT ON GOING.
HE MAY NOT LIKE IT,
BUT I KNOW IT'S THERE.
WE'RE GONNA GET GOLD.
THERE'S GONNA BE BIG GOLD.
I KNOW WHERE IT'S AT.
I JUST CAN'T JUMP
STRAIGHT INTO IT.
NO MATTER WHAT
TODD HOFFMAN SAYS.
-WELL, NO MATTER...
-WE'RE STICKING TO IT.
WE'RE GONNA GO FOR BROKE.
**
Fred: WE COULD CERTAINLY FIND
THE 20 OUNCES THERE
PLUS A WHOLE LOT MORE
IF WE CAN GET DOWN
TO THE BOTTOM.
EVEN ONE POCKET OF GOLD,
I MEAN,
WE'RE TALKING MAYBE HUNDREDS
AND HUNDREDS OF OUNCES.
Narrator:
FRED AND DUSTIN BELIEVE
THE LIFE-CHANGING GOLD
IS BURIED DEEP ON THE BEDROCK
BELOW McKINLEY CREEK.
OVER THE LAST 10,000 YEARS,
RUSHING GLACIAL MELTWATER
HAS CARVED THE CREEK
OUT OF THE BEDROCK.
THE WATER HAS ALSO CARRIED
BOULDERS AND GRAVEL,
DEPOSITING THEM
ALONG THE CREEK BED.
WITH THE ROCKS CAME GOLD.
SEVEN TIMES HEAVIER,
SO IT SANK TO THE BEDROCK,
CREATING LARGE DEPOSITS,
WHICH DUSTIN BELIEVES
ARE FEET BELOW
WHERE THEY'RE DREDGING.
GOLD'S HEAVIER THAN
EVERYTHING ELSE OUT HERE,
SO IT'S GONNA WANNA SINK
ITSELF DOWN TO THE BOTTOM.
SO THE DEEPER WE GO,
THE MORE GOLD WE'LL FIND.
Dustin: ALL RIGHT, CARLOS.
THAT'S ABOUT 8 FEET.
LET'S MAKE SURE
WE GET TO 12 FEET TODAY,
ALL RIGHT?
-ALL RIGHT.
I'D LIKE TO SEE THIS
WHOLE THING UNDERWATER TODAY.
-ALL RIGHT.
-READY TO ROCK AND ROLL.
Carlos: I GOTTA GET TO
PROCESSING UNDERNEATH.
Dustin:
OKAY, UH, YOU GET GLOVES.
I'LL GET ON COMMS.
DON'T LET HIM FALL.
**
ALL RIGHT, THERE.
THIS IS DUSTIN.
I'LL BE YOUR OPERATOR
FOR TODAY.
ROGER, ROGER.
I'M UNDERWATER.
OH.
-[ LAUGHS ]
-OH.
-DUDE, IT'S COLD.
I KNOW IT'S COLD.
**
HOW YOU DOING DOWN THERE,
CARLOS?
YEAH, YEAH.
UH, WELL, YOU'RE
DOING GREAT, MAN.
JUST KEEP IT UP.
-ALL RIGHT.
THERE'S A WHOLE BUNCH
OF DIRT COMING OUT OF HERE.
THESE GUYS ARE LEARNING
AND TRENCHING.
THEY'RE JUST
GETTING GREAT AT IT.
HE'S GOT
A WONDERFUL PACE.
[ GRUNTS ]
YOU ALL RIGHT?
[ LAUGHS ]
CARLOS KEEPS GETTING
STUCK INSIDE THE DREDGE.
IT'S HILARIOUS.
Paul: YEP, I SEE IT COMING
OVER THE SLUICE.
LOOKS GOOD.
WHENEVER YOU GET TIRED,
JUST LET US KNOW.
YEAH, YEAH.
FIND THAT GOLD, MAN.
IT'S DOWN THERE.
WE JUST GOTTA GET IT.
Narrator: THE DREDGE IS NOT
DESIGNED TO REMOVE ROCKS BIGGER
THAN 6 INCHES ACROSS.
WE GOT A SYSTEM WHERE YOU THROW
ROCKS INTO A BASKET, FILL IT UP.
WE POP IT OUT, DUMP IT,
PUT IT RIGHT BACK.
ALL RIGHT.
HE'S INCOMING.
IT'LL BE DOWN INTO
THE WATER VERY SOON.
OKAY. THAT'S IT.
YOU GOT IT. GOOD TO GO.
IT'S SO MUCH WORK
TO MOVE ALL THIS ROCK.
EVERYTHING WE DO
IS PHYSICAL LABOR.
AND IT'S SOME HARD WORK.
WE'RE GETTING THERE
A ROCK AT A TIME.
WHAT HAPPENED?
NEED TO GET TO THE BOTTOM
OF THIS [BLEEP]
BECAUSE THAT'S
THE END GOAL HERE.
LET'S SEE WHAT
YOU CAN DO, MAN.
[ LAUGHS ]
DAMN.
THAT'S A GOOD ROCK.
[ LAUGHS ]
WE'VE MOVED
SOME BIG-ASS ROCKS, MAN.
UGH [BLEEP]
UGH.
CARLOS.
PULL ME UP.
[ GRUNTING ]
OH, GRAVITY.
AAH.
IT GOT HIS HAND.
-DID HE?
-YEAH.
LOOK AT THAT
MOTHER [BLEEP], DUDE.
AH. IT WAS A ROCK
BOULDER SANDWICH,
AND MY FINGER
WAS THE MEAT.
THAT'S ONE OF
OUR BIGGEST PROBLEMS
IS FINGER-SMASHING OUT HERE.
CAN'T LIFT BOULDERS
WITH A BUSTED HAND.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
LET'S CALL IT A DAY.
WE NEED A FASTER,
SAFER WAY TO MOVE
BOULDERS AND ROCKS.
Carlos: YEAH, MAN. I JUST --
I DIDN'T REALIZE
HOW MANY FREAKING BOULDERS
ARE DOWN THERE, MAN.
YOU KNOW,
PICK ONE BOULDER UP
WITHOUT MAKING A FREAKING
FINGER SANDWICHES
WITH THOSE DAMN THINGS.
WE NEED SOME SORT OF DEVICE.
TRY TO THINK OF A WAY
TO SAVE OUR HANDS
AND GET US
MOVING ROCKS FASTER.
Fred:
I RUN OUT OF STEAM QUICK.
I'D RATHER LET
A MECHANICAL DEVICE
HELP ME OUT
ANY TIME I CAN.
LOOK. I GOT A FEW LITTLE IDEAS,
UH, SOMETHING TO --
YOU GOTTA HAVE SOMETHING
TO GET AROUND THEM ROCKS,
SOMETHING
THAT'LL GO BEHIND IT.
OR WHATEVER YOU CAN
COME UP WITH,
I'M LEAVING IT UP TO YOU.
IF WE DON'T MOVE
THESE ROCKS IN THIS DIRT,
UH,
WE DON'T GET TO BEDROCK.
WE DON'T GET GOLD.
WE NEED TO GET THIS DONE.
[ MOTOR STARTS ]
I NEVER HAD TO BUILD ANYTHING
LIKE THIS AT ALL BEFORE.
THIS IS MY FIRST ATTEMPT
AT SOME KIND OF
A GRABBER-TYPE DEVICE.
WE'RE JUST MAKING IT
OUT OF STUFF
THAT WE HAVE AVAILABLE HERE.
IN THIS CASE, I HAVE
A NUMBER OF FENCE POSTS.
Narrator: FRED'S PLAN --
THE GRABBER'S GIANT HOOKS
WILL REACH
BENEATH THE BOULDER.
USING THE OVERHEAD WINCH SYSTEM,
IT SHOULD LIFT THE BOULDER UP
AND CLEAR OF THE DIVE POOL.
I'M A TERRIBLE WELDER.
BUT, UH, I CAN STICK
TWO PIECES OF METAL TOGETHER.
HELL,
I USED TO WELD UNDERWATER.
WHEN WE WAS CUTTING,
WE WOULD CRANK --
CRANK A WELDING MACHINE
UP TO 300 AMPS.
OCCASIONALLY YOU WOULD
GET SHOCKED PRETTY BAD.
SO GET A LITTLE SHOCK
OUT OF A LITTLE
WET STUFF HERE,
NO BIG DEAL.
HAPPENS ALL THE TIME.
IT'S NOT GONNA LOOK GLORIOUS.
IF IT WORKS,
THAT'S ALL I CARE ABOUT.
**
YEAH, MY WELDING
LOOKS LIKE DOG TURDS.
MAN, I CAN'T WAIT TO GET
TO DOWN HERE TO CAMP.
Narrator:
AT McKINLEY CREEK,
FRED HURT HAS BUILT
A DEVICE TO TACKLE
THE BOULDERS BLOCKING
THEIR PATH TO THE GOLD.
WHAT YOU GOT, FRED?
THIS IS JUST A DEVICE
THAT'S GONNA GRAB THE ROCKS.
LIKE A -- LIKE A CHAIN BASKET
BASICALLY.
I KNOW IT LOOKS, UH,
INCREDIBLY CRUDE.
YOU KNOW THIS THING
LOOKS CRAZY, RIGHT?
IT LOOKS ABSOLUTELY GORY.
BUT, UH, LET ME
TELL YOU WHAT.
THEM ROCKS DOWN THERE
ARE GORY.
IT LOOKS LIKE SOMETHING
OUT OF A NIGHTMARE, FRED.
IT DOES.
MADE IT OUT OF
SOME HEAVY STEEL, HUH?
YEAH. WELL, SOME OF THE ROCKS
WE GOTTA MOVE...
WELL...
I'M NOT CARRYING IT
OVER THERE.
IT'S, UH, PIG STEEL.
I NEED SOMETHING
THAT'S MADE OUT OF SOMETHING
A LITTLE LESS HEAVY.
I GOTTA PICK THIS THING UP
100 TIMES A DAY.
I'M ALR--
I MIGHT AS WELL LIFT ROCKS,
I'MA LIFT THAT DAMN THING.
**
Narrator: FRED'S FORCED
TO CONTINUE DIVING,
BUT WITH NO WAY
TO REMOVE THE BOULDERS.
Fred: OH [BLEEP]
SON OF A [BLEEP]
Carlos:
HEY, UH, HEY, FRED.
Wes:
HOLY [BLEEP], MAN.
**
[ BLEEP ]
-DANG, MAN.
-YOU LOOK LIKE A GIANT ELK.
THAT TOOK A LOT OF EFFORT
TO GET THAT THING OVER HERE.
Dustin: IT'S NOT THE HEAVIEST
THING I CARRIED,
BUT IT'S THE MOST AWKWARD.
GETTING BETTER AT IT.
WHAT THE [BLEEP]
AH, YOU MADE --
YOU DEFINITELY
MADE HISTORY FOR ME.
THAT'S THE MOST AWKWARD HIKE
I'VE EVER HAD IN MY LIFE.
I'M GONNA TELL YOU WHAT.
WE COULD'VE USED THAT THING
A HALF DOZEN TIMES TODAY.
WELL...
GET THAT DAMN THING
OFF YOUR BACK.
LOOK LIKE A [BLEEP]
DAMN ELK.
[ LAUGHS ]
PUT YOUR [BLEEP]
LOOK LIKE A TRANSFORMER.
I'LL BE DAMNED.
-OOH.
BROUGHT THIS BECAUSE
I SAW THE LIGHTS
IN FRED'S EYES GO OUT.
I FELT SO DAMN BAD.
I HAD TO BRING IT.
HERE WE GO.
HERE'S THE MAIDEN VOYAGE.
BE KIND OF INTERESTING
TO SEE HOW IT WORKS.
Fred: ALL RIGHT.
WE GET THAT GRABBER,
IT'S COMING DOWN
TOWARDS YOU RIGHT THERE.
JUST SEE WHAT YOU
CAN DO WITH IT.
ARE YOU READY
TO PULL IT?
-YEAH.
-ALL RIGHT.
HOW 'BOUT DO YOU EVER SAY,
"OKAY?"
Dustin: SAID IT SIX TIMES,
"OKAY, OKAY, OKAY, OKAY, OKAY,
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY, OKAY."
TRY IT ONE MORE TIME,
DUSTIN.
JUST TRY IT ONE MORE TIME.
ABSOLUTELY.
I'LL KEEP TRYING.
-TRY IT AGAIN.
SEE WHAT IT'S GONNA DO.
Fred: TRYING TO PULL THESE ROCKS
OUT OF HERE IS VERY DIFFICULT.
UH, HEY, SOMETIMES IT WORKS.
SOMETIMES IT DON'T.
SOMETIMES
YOUR IDEAS ARE GOOD.
THEY AIN'T SO GOOD.
**
Narrator: ONE DAY AFTER
FRED'S GRABBER FAILED,
WES HAS FABRICATED
HIS OWN BOULDER DEVICE.
-YEAH.
-CAN I GET SOME ASSISTANCE
TO GET THIS OFF MY BACK
FROM SOMEBODY, PLEASE?
-WHAT YOU GOT HERE?
-FRED, THIS IS THE CLAW.
YEP. LOOKS LIKE SOME
BIG OL' FINGERS THERE.
SO IT LOOKS
JUST LIKE A CLAW.
WE'RE GONNA CLAW THEM ROCKS
AND PULL THEM RIGHT OUT.
I MEAN, THEY ARE
OUR ACHILLES HEELS OUT THERE.
YEP. WE'LL GIVE IT A SHOT
AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS, ANYWAY.
ALL RIGHT. GOOD.
I'M EAGER TO SEE
THAT THING WORK, MAN.
WES' CLAW IS LIGHTER
AND WIDER THAN FRED'S GRABBER.
IF DUSTIN CAN'T GET IT
TO PICK UP THE BOULDERS,
THEY'LL NEVER GET
TO BEDROCK GOLD.
**
Fred: YEP, STAND BY.
WES' CLAW HOOKED UP
ONTO YOUR, UH, LINE HERE.
Dustin: [ BLEEP ]
WE'RE STRUGGLING.
WE ARE STRUGGLING.
THERE'S NO DOUBT OF IT.
AH [BLEEP]
YOU READY?
[ BLEEP ]
COME BACK AGAIN.
ARE YOU READY?
-YES!
-ALL RIGHT. THAT'S ALL I NEED.
WE'RE COMING UP.
HERE IT GOES.
ALL RIGHT.
YEAH, WE GOT A STRAIN.
COME ON, BABY.
WE GOT IT.
WE GOT IT. WE GOT IT.
GREAT.
WE GOT IT, MAN.
WE GOT IT. WE GOT IT.
GOOD JOB THERE, DUSTIN.
GREAT JOB, MAN.
-THAT'S A BIG ROCK.
NOW, WE GOTTA GET IT
DOWNSTREAM.
HERE COMES THE FUN PART.
[ MACHINE REVVING ]
Narrator:
WES HAS ADAPTED A CHAINSAW
TO WINCH THE BOULDERS
CLEAR OF THE DIVE SITE.
WHOO, THAT'S [BLEEP]
GOOD, BRO.
[ LAUGHS ] WHOO-HOO!
Wes:
YOU KNOW, WE'VE GOT TO GET
THE MOST OUT OF
EVERY MINUTE OUT HERE.
TIME IS GOLD
AND GOLD IS MONEY.
Narrator: UP AHEAD...
Wes: THIS MIGHT BE ONE
OF THE BIGGEST ROCKS
THAT WE'VE TRIED TO PULL
WITH OUR CHAIN WINCH SO FAR.
Fred: WHOA.
I THINK OUR GENERATOR'S
ABOUT TO QUIT.
IT'S SURGING BAD.
-HEY, THE WINCH IS ON FIRE.
THE WINCH IS ON FIRE.
**
Fred: GOTTA GET READY TO GO
OUT THERE AND GO OUR --
DO OUR THING AGAIN TODAY.
Narrator: AT McKINLEY CREEK,
THE DAKOTA BOYS
ARE ATTEMPTING TO BREAK THROUGH
A LAYER OF BOULDERS
TO GET TO A PILE OF GOLD
ON BEDROCK.
Fred:
THERE'S NO VISIBILITY TODAY.
BUT YOU KNOW
I'D DIVE IN THIS.
KIND OF LIKE MAKING LOVE
TO A WOMAN IN THE DARK.
YOU JUST GOTTA KIND OF FEEL
YOUR WAY AROUND.
**
Carlos: STAND BY, FRED.
ALL RIGHT.
GOT YOU LOUD AND CLEAR.
HOW YOU GOT ME?
-YEAH, I'M FINE.
-ROGER, ROGER.
Dustin:
HE'S GONNA PUT THAT WINCH
ON THAT BIG [BLEEP] ROCK.
-ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
-HE WON'T STOP.
THIS MIGHT BE ONE
OF THE BIGGEST ROCKS
THAT WE'VE TRIED TO PULL
WITH OUR CHAIN WINCH SO FAR,
SO I HOPE IT'S GONNA PULL IT.
Dustin:
FRED WANTS TO LIFT SOMETHING
THAT MIGHT BE 1,000 POUNDS.
AND ALL THESE CABLES
AND PULLEYS
CAN JUST EXPLODE
AND FLY EVERYWHERE.
UM,
IF ANYONE'S GONNA DIE HERE,
THIS IS HOW THEY'RE GONNA DIE.
Narrator:
TO REMOVE THIS HALF-TON BOULDER
THAT'S STOPPING THEM
GETTING TO BEDROCK GOLD,
FRED'S DECIDED TO STRAP
A CABLE AROUND IT
AND LIFT IT UP OUT OF THE CREEK
USING THE OVERHEAD WINCH SYSTEM.
THE CABLES HAVE A SAFE
WORKING LOAD OF 1,400 POUNDS.
BUT IF ANY OF THE ANCHOR
POINTS FAIL...
...THE CABLE AND ANCHORS
COULD FLY ACROSS THE CREEK
WITH LETHAL FORCE.
HEY, FRED. UH, I SEE YOU
HOOKING THAT THING UP.
UH, I HAVE TO EVACUATE
EVERYBODY OUT OF HERE.
UH, SO NOBODY'S GONNA GET HURT.
YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN.
WE'LL WALKING OUT
FOR A MINUTE.
ALL RIGHT?
-GO AHEAD.
ALL RIGHT.
LAST CONTACT.
YES. I CAN HEAR
EVERYTHING YOU SAY.
ALL RIGHT.
COME UP.
GET OUT OF THERE.
COME HERE. UP.
OUT.
Carlos: THIS IS GONNA BE SCARY,
BROTHER.
GET OUT OF THERE.
DON'T MAKE ME [BLEEP]
SAY IT AGAIN.
AND YOU NEED
TO GET OUTTA THERE.
THAT'S A BIG,
BIG BOULDER DOWN THERE.
THAT COMES DOWN,
IT HIT ANYBODY
IN THE HEAD AND THAT --
THEY WOULD BE DONE.
THIS IS ALL PRETTY SKETCHY.
THIS IS CRAZY.
Narrator: ONCE THE CREW IS CLEAR
OF THE DANGER ZONE,
DUSTIN CAN OPERATE
THE REMOTE WINCH.
Fred: THE ROCK IS
MOVING RIGHT NOW.
KEEP GOING.
WHOA.
I NEED MORE POWER.
MAKE SURE IT'S NOT TRIPPING.
[ MACHINE WHIRRING,
SPUTTERING ]
I THINK WE MAXED IT OUT.
I DON'T THINK IT'LL LIFT IT.
IT'S GONNA BREAK HER.
-THE GENERATOR'S ABOUT TO QUIT.
IT'S SURGING BAD.
-HEY, THE WINCH IS ON FIRE.
THE WINCH IS ON FIRE.
Narrator:
THE WINCH SYSTEM IS MAXED OUT.
THE BOULDER IS NOW STUCK.
[ BLEEP ] DAMN IT.
**
[ BLEEP ]
THAT'S A BAD SITUATION
RIGHT THERE, MAN.
Narrator:
THE ENTIRE 1,000-POUND LOAD
DEPENDS ON JUST THREE
SMALL ANCHOR POINTS.
**
COME-ALONG. HEY.
COME-ALONG.
WHERE'S THE COME-ALONG?
-HERE'S ONE.
-OKAY. COOL.
DUSTIN PLANS TO USE
A COME-ALONG
TO MANUALLY RATCHET
THE BOULDER OUT...
...PUTTING MORE STRAIN
ON THE CABLES
AND ANCHOR POINTS.
[ BLEEP ] DAMN, I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M DOING THIS.
INSANE.
THEY GOT A ANCHOR POINT.
WE'VE GOT A COME-ALONG.
WE CAN'T USE THE WINCH.
SO WE'RE JUST GONNA USE
THAT ANCHOR POINT
AND PULL THAT BOULDER
ACROSS.
THIS IS GHETTO FRED
AS A GHETTO FRED GETS.
Paul: OKAY. THEY'RE STARTING
TO PULL IT OVER NOW.
THAT'S NOT GONNA...
WE'RE GOOD.
IT JUST SHIFTED.
**
THERE IT IS.
THERE IT COMES.
THAT'S
A PRETTY GOOD-SIZED ROCK.
GHETTO!
YES,
THAT'S WHAT I'M GONNA DO.
DON'T SNAP ON ME, PLEASE.
Fred: GETTING SOMETHING GOOD
THERE.
YEP.
-[ BLEEP ]
CARLOS HAS THE LOOK
OF FEAR IN HIS EYES THOUGH.
-YEAH, I KNOW.
-NEED TO --
[ BLEEP ]
WHOO!
THAT'S A LOADED GUN, DUDE.
-YES, IT IS.
THIS IS HOW PEOPLE DIE.
-SURPRISE!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, FRED.
-HAPPY BIRTHDAY, FRED.
Woman: HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
-OH.
-73 AND STILL KICKING BUTT, MAN.
-WHOO.
-I KNOW 25-YEAR-OLDS
THAT CAN'T DO
WHAT YOU DID TODAY, MAN.
CAN -- CAN I SLOBBER ON IT?
NICE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Narrator: 73-YEAR-OLD FRED
HAS A SURPRISE OF HIS OWN.
ALL RIGHT.
LET ME HAVE YOUR ATTENTION.
JENN AND I
ARE GETTING MARRIED...
-YEAH.
-...IN 2 WEEKS.
-ALL RIGHT.
-CONGRATULATIONS, FRED.
CONGRATULATIONS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
LET 'EM GET MARRIED.
HELL, WHY NOT?
THAT'S WHAT HE DOES.
I THINK THIS IS
HIS FOURTH OR FIFTH TIME.
[ LAUGHS ]
-THAT'S YOUR BIRTHDAY CROWN.
-THIS IS YOUR BIRTHDAY CROWN.
-OH, BOY. HOLY CRAP.
-AND YOU MUST WEAR IT.
Fred: LOOK AT ALL THEM
LITTLE NUGGETS UP THERE.
-YEAH.
-WONDER WHERE THEY COME FROM.
NOT OUT OF OUR SLUICE BOX
YET.
[ LAUGHS ]
**
[ GRUNTS ]
Narrator:
THE DAKOTA BOYS ARE DIGGING DOWN
TO McKINLEY CREEK GOLD
ONE BOULDER AT A TIME.
**
GOOD TO GO.
LET'S DO THIS, MAN.
BACK TO
THE HOLE OF WONDERS.
YEAH, MAN.
Dustin:
COMING UP ON THE CLAW.
Dustin: CARLOS IS ROCKING
THE BOULDERS TODAY.
**
[ BLEEP ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
Dustin:
WELL, DOES THAT PAY WELL,
THAT WHOLE ROCK-MOVING THING?
HELL, NO. NOT YET. IT WILL.
Narrator:
THE CREW HAS CLEARED DOZENS
OF BOULDERS FROM THE DIVE POOL.
IT'S TIME TO CHECK
HOW DEEP THEY'VE GOTTEN.
Carlos: EIGHT FEET.
YOU KNOW.
IT'S 10 FEET DEEP.
IT'S GETTING PRETTY DEEP.
Paul:
THIS COULD BE THE MOMENT.
CARLOS WORKS RIGHT THERE
WHERE HE'S AT
AND GOES DOWN TO THE BOTTOM,
IT COULD BE A BIG PAYDAY
RIGHT THERE.
Dustin: CARLOS, TODAY, HAS
ALREADY MADE A LOT OF PROGRESS.
I STILL HAVEN'T SEEN PAYOFF.
I'VE ALWAYS KNOWN,
IN MY HEAD AND HEART,
THAT IT'S THERE.
Paul:
OKAY. HE'S COMING UP.
HE'S DONE. PULL HIM UP.
MOVED A LOT OF ROCKS
AND A LOT OF DIRT TODAY.
IT'S PROBABLY
OUR BEST DAY YET.
SEEING SOME GOLD OUT --
OUT OF THIS STUFF
WOULD BE GREAT.
JUST A LITTLE BIT
WOULD HELP.
WE'RE GONNA DO A CLEAN-UP.
Narrator: THE CREW HAS REMOVED
ANOTHER 2 FEET
OF GRAVEL AND BOULDERS,
BUT THEY'VE STILL
NOT HIT BEDROCK.
ANY GOLD NOW WILL BE
A SIGN OF THE JACKPOT
THAT LIES BENEATH.
Paul: THIS IS GONNA BE
INTERESTING.
-SEE ANYTHING?
-OH, WAIT A MINUTE.
THERE'S A LITTLE NUGGET
IN HERE.
LOOK AT THAT.
**
SOMEBODY FOUND SOME GOLD.
NICE LITTLE NUGGET.
FRED, THIS JUST
A LITTLE PIECE OF GOLD.
Fred: HOO, LITTLE OL' BITTY
THING. OH, LORD.
IT'S MORE THAN I THOUGHT
WE'D GET OUT OF THIS
BECAUSE
IT'S STILL OVERBURDEN.
**
I'LL BE DANGED.
WE COULD GO FOR 3, 4 WEEKS
AND NOT FIND A SPECK OF GOLD.
AND THEN ONE WEEK,
WE COULD COME UP
WITH 50 OUNCES, YOU KNOW?
OH, I HOPE
WE GOT SOME GOLD.
GIVE IT A COUPLE MINUTES HERE
AND SEE WHAT WE END UP WITH.
HOW'S IT LOOKING?
-YEAH, THERE'S GOLD IN IT.
-THERE'S A NICE LITTLE CHUNK.
Wes: THAT'S ACTUALLY
PRETTY GOOD, YOU KNOW.
I'M PRETTY HAPPY WITH, UH,
WHAT I SEE COMING OUT OF HERE.
GET A PAN SO WE CAN GET
THAT STUFF OUT AND SEE.
HEY, FRED.
COME CHECK THIS OUT.
HEY, GUYS.
-WHATCHA GOT?
TAKE A LOOK.
Wes: OH, THAT'S NOT SO BAD
FOR THE HEIGHT
OF THE AREA WE WERE DREDGING.
I MEAN, WHAT'S
THE DEEPEST YOU GOT?
10 FEET.
WE'RE NOT REALLY GONNA KNOW
UNTIL WE CAN GET TO THE BEDROCK.
Fred: I SAY WE JUST STAY ON IT,
KEEP AFTER IT AND, UH,
WE DO THE BEST
WE CAN WITH IT.
WE'RE ACTUALLY JUST GETTING
GOING IN THAT HOLE.
-YEP.
-IT -- IT'S THERE. IT'S THERE.
I'M SURE IT IS.
WE HAVEN'T FOUND
THAT POCKET OF GOLD YET.
I'M GONNA BE STILL
LOOKING FOR THAT
VERY DEEPEST PART
OF THAT BEDROCK.
HEY, I'M KIND
OF OLD-SCHOOL.
I KNOW SOMETIMES IT TAKES
A LOT OF WORK, PATIENCE.
BUT IT PAYS OFF IN THE END.
PERSISTENCE, MAN.
PERSISTENCE.
**
Dustin: IT'S A GREAT AREA,
AND IT'S -- THE SIGNS ARE GREAT.
BUT IT'S LIKE A PUZZLE.
WHERE WOULD YOU GO
IF YOU WERE GOLD?
TRY TO THINK LIKE GOLD.
WOULD IT SIT RIGHT HERE?
WOULD IT SIT RIGHT THERE?
WHY THE HELL WOULD YOU SIT
RIGHT THERE AND NOT RIGHT THERE?
THINK MAYBE IF I STARE
AT IT LONG ENOUGH,
I COULD FIGURE IT OUT.
I KNOW THERE'S GOLD THERE.
JUST NEED TO GET DEEPER.
**
Narrator:
ON THE NEXT EPISODE...
-ALL RIGHT. HERE WE GO.
-FIND ME SOME GOLD!
Dustin: LANDSLIDE.
IT'S COMPLETELY
ACROSS THE CREEK.
IF IT COMES OVER THE TOP
OF THAT AND BUSTS THROUGH,
IT WILL KICK OUR ASS.
WE COULD GET, UH,
LIKE A TSUNAMI.
THE WATER DROPPED 10 INCHES
IN A COUPLE MINUTES.
THAT MEANS THERE'S A WALL
OF WATER GONNA COME.
WE RUN FOR THE HILLS
AS FAST AS WE CAN.
Carlos:
WE GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE.
**
I'M GOING TO GET
MY GOLD THIS WEEKEND.
Man:
YOU MAY KISS YOUR BRIDE.