(slow and tense music)
(screaming)
God damn it!
[Gina] Hold him down!
He shot me!
Yeah, that's what you get!
I wasn't gonna shot anybody!
You were still acting like an ass.
We're gonna need to stitch this up.
Alex, can you go get the first aid kit?
Gina?
[Gina] We're not gonna
be those people, Alex.
We're better than them.
(groaning)
He's gonna be fine.
Go fuck yourself!
(groaning)
This is gonna hurt.
(groaning loudly)
(breathing deeply)
Thank you.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, don't do that.
Why not?
We don't know what going on out there,
it could be anything.
Reactive contamination, super bacteria.
Synthetic virus attacks
for population containment.
I miss drinking rain water.
David, have you taken a look outside?
Catiline hasn't been affected.
For all we know, the
impact could be something
significantly smaller than expected.
This could be just a
communications blackout.
We don't know what it is.
I know what I saw, alright?
Whoever attacked make
that school out there
something straight out of
the Book of Revelations!
You were attacked?
Yeah, Alex, I was attacked, alright?
Now I'm pretty sure,
they were zombies.
David, have you lost your mind?
Look, just hear me out, alright?
No!
I've heard enough of your conspiracy crap.
Look, you ask those
two out there, alright?
I'm sure they've seen it.
This isn't the time for pacifism.
I brought this for you.
We don't need that.
We need to know what happened.
What's there to tell?
Cut the shit, just tell
us what happened out there.
David, stop it.
No, this guy and his girlfriend trek
all the way down here to
hold up in an abandon ranch
and attack the owners?
I wanna know why.
And he's going to tell us, right?
His name is Curtis.
Thank you.
Yes, I'm Curtis.
This is Apple.
[David] Apple?
Yeah, right.
Listen, it's simple.
The impact was big.
How big?
Entire Eastern seaboard big.
Government, law, order,
it's all gone, you guys.
Worked out pretty
good for you, didn't it?
You wanna know something funny, David?
I'm a sheriff's deputy.
I was on corrections
detail when we got back in.
Prison guard.
[David] Was she your prisoner?
She did deputy too.
Why don't you let me hear her say that?
Oh, you don't talk much, do you?
What brought you here?
As you can imagine, it's
kinda hard to run a prison
during the apocalypse.
Wasn't long after the power ran out
the entire place was overrun.
(horns blaring)
Stay still.
(growling)
(deep exhaling)
I think we're good.
(screaming)
(gun firing)
We got out just in time.
It's not pretty out there.
The world you guys knew is gone.
What about the fucking zombies?
Excuse me?
Not this again.
Look, I know what I saw and I know
that he's seen them too!
That's why you're on this island!
You're fucking in on it.
Sheriff's department?
You're probably CIA!
Are you out of your fucking mind?
What is it, huh?
Population control?
Genocide, government virus?
Fucking tell me!
David!
Put a leech on your dog, Curtis.
David, calm down.
[David] Nah, this guy's a fucking liar!
We all need to calm down.
It's been a long day, we all need sleep.
It's been a long day.
Go.
(footsteps retreating)
(gun clocking)
Shh.
You're gonna fucking talk
or I'm gonna kill you.
You're not gonna kill me.
Oh, I'm not gonna kill you?
David!
Stay back!
Get off of him!
Stay out of this, Alex, you don't want
any part of this!
Maybe but this is not the way!
I'm finding out the truth!
Whether you believe me or not,
there's something going on
out there and this guy knows what!
What do you wanna know?
Are there zombies?
OK, I'll tell you
anything you wanna know!
(gun firing)
(serene music)