(brooding music)
("The Z Virus" opening theme music)
(eerie tense music)
Fuck!
(zombie growling)
Aw shit!
Who is that?
(mumbling)
How many are out there?
It's just one, one man!
Screw this!
Excuse me!
(mumbles) me!
Hi-ya!
(squishing)
(zombie growling)
(thumping)
(growling)
(tense music)
Who are you?
Uh, my uh, my name is,
is Eddie Gomez, and I'm a,
or I was a doctor back in Phoenix.
Phoenix, how'd you get here?
It wasn't easy.
What's it like back on the mainlands?
Look you guys need to listen to me here,
and listen to me very clearly.
We need to barricade that door,
and we need to board
up these windows, okay?
Do whatever it takes to secure
this house, they're coming.
- Who's coming?
- Who do you think?
The fucking zombies man!
They're already here pal.
What?
Yeah, your buddy's out there
walking around on the porch.
Aw, okay, um, uh...
I thought I gave him the
slip back in Avalon but uh,
but I guess I, I ran into a herd,
a few miles back and, I uh,
I guess they tracked me here.
[Curtis] Tracked you?
Yeah, you guys really
need to listen to me.
There's, there's more of them, a lot more,
and they're coming!
That's what they do!
If one of them finds you, they uh,
they attract a swarm of them, okay?
[Curtis] And I have just
one or two more questions.
No no no, listen!
Look hey, I'm not here to argue with you,
I'm here to tell you what to
do in order for us to survive!
Okay doc, we'll follow your lead.
(zombies growling)
Okay.
(clattering)
Easy, easy, easy!
What's the weapon situation like guys?
We have guns?
Huh, there wasn't time doc.
What's that supposed to mean?
We have guns, they're
just locked up at my bunker.
Well where's that?
About 300 yards from here.
[Eddie] (sighs) Well shit.
[Curtis] I told you
that was a stupid idea.
These zombies don't
seem to be too quick.
Maybe I could make a run for it.
- Alex!
- Don't be fooled man,
these things will pick up speed
as soon as they get excited!
Anything agitates them,
it'll, it'll flip a switch.
There's just one.
Yes, speaking of which.
- Dad!
- What Nicole?
I don't think you're gonna have enough
time to get to the bunker.
What does that mean?
(zombies growling)
(zombies snarling)
- You saw how tough just one
was, we can't fight that many.
I'm going for the guns.
No you're not Alex!
[Alex] Gina it's the only way!
What, and leave us here
to fight those things off?
Curtis, with three women and a cripple?
She's right guys, we need
to keep all the muscle here.
I'll go.
[Curtis] Apple, you're not going.
I'm the best chance
we've got, I'm going.
She's right, it's our only choice.
(zombies growling)
(zombies snarling)
(tense music)
Okay, once you're through
the grove, turn west.
The entrance to the bunker
will be about 200 yards
from the side of the hill.
Ready!
(clanking)
(growling)
Apple, go!
(dramatic music)
(zombie snarling)
(Nicole squealing)
Nicole!
(thumping)
Nicole, Nicole, get to the bunker now!
(squishing)
Apple, go!
Get Nicole to the bunker!
(zombies growling)
(zombies snarling)
[Nicole] Are we supposed
to take all of them?
As many as I can carry.
This is a Ruger SR9 nine millimeter pistol
with a laser scope on top.
Why are you giving me a gun?
Because no one else has.
This isn't like your little video game,
the TV shows you used to watch.
You're going to be fighting
for your survival out there.
You're just making me
nervous, I'm not ready--
(mumbles) Look at me!
You have to be ready for this.
Seriously though, I've
never killed anybody before!
Neither had I until a few nights ago.
Release the safety here
and pull back the chamber
and load the rounds in, aim
at what you want to shoot at,
and then, pull the trigger.
Pull the trigger?
- Apple!
- Yeah.
Thank you.
This is all I could find.
(thumping)
(zombie growling)
- We got one in the kitchen!
(Curtis growling)
(zombie growling)
(thumping)
Oh shit, oh shit!
Get something!
(Gina screaming)
(thumping)
(zombie growling)
(mumbling)
Ya!
(thumping)
[Eddie] Zombies on the right!
(zombies growling)
(tense music)
[Alex] Ya, get out, get out!
(scuffling)
(zombie growling)
(gun firing)
Aah!
Nicole?
Like I told Mom, it's
the end of the world.
What did you expect?
(zombies growling)
(muffled slamming)
(eerie tense music)
("The Z Virus" closing theme music)