(intense music)
(screen door creaking)
Thank you, is that what you wanna hear?
What then, I'm not apologizing
for that, neither should you.
Crazy fucker got what he deserved.
They can act all shocked.
If you hadn't pulled the
trigger, one of them would've.
Maybe not today, maybe not
tomorrow but eventually.
Eventually that crazy bastard
would've gotten to them all.
Give me a break, why
are you on their side?
You know this isn't helping them right?
All they know is gone, it's changed.
I'm not here to make friends.
For you, I'll be cordial, I'll play nice.
I'm not anyone's friend.
Whatever, you really
need to start talking.
This mind shit's getting old.
(ax slamming against wood)
(intense music)
(water pouring)
Alex, are we gonna talk?
I'm really not ready to, Jan.
And neither is your daughter
and I think that's bullshit.
Now more than ever, we need to
rely on each other for support.
I've got a lot to process.
I don't even know what
I'm gonna do about them.
That's why you have me.
It's not that simple, babe.
It is, we're letting them stay.
- Are you crazy?
- You married me
because you know I am, they stay.
Whether you want to admit it or not,
that girl killing David
was the right thing to do.
- Gina.
- This is where we
are right now, Alex, a harsh
road of tough decisions
ahead of us, each one more
difficult than the next.
And the last thing we need is doubts.
My husband, the father of my
child doesn't have doubts.
He acts and he reacts.
I'm trying to be a good man.
You are a good man in a bad situation.
(intense music)
(screen door creaking)
I've agreed to let you two stay.
Well, we appreciate
that, dibs on the couch.
There will be some concessions made.
- Such as?
- The guns.
Hand them over.
- Absolutely not.
- It's non-negotiable.
- Try and take 'em from me.
- They'll go in my lock
up with my other guns.
Neither one of us will be carrying until
we both feel comfortable with each other.
Who's got the only key, I wonder.
You can have it.
I'm trying to double cross you, Curtis.
I'm trying to make sure neither one of us
gets heated enough to recreate
last night, work with me.
(sighs)
(intense music)
(door creaking)
You got enough guns, Alex?
- Always be prepared.
(intense music)
For the record, this is a bad idea.
(door creaking shut)
(rustling leaves)
So where are you guys from?
How long have you guys lived here?
Quite some time now,
actually I'm from Jamecula.
Now Gina, she's an Islander.
Her parents originally owned this place.
Yeah, we lived here for
a few years and then my
parents took us back to Avalon.
[Limping Man] Anybody
in the fuckin' house?
(slamming on door)
Is anybody in there?
- What the hell?
- Let me in please.
- Expecting someone?
(intense music)
[Limping Man] Open up, please.
- Alex.
- Please let me in.
They're coming.
- Who's coming, pal?
Who do you think, just
open the door for God's sake.
We can't leave him out there.
- Oh, yes we can.
- No, we can't.
(sighs)
- Jesus Christ.
- Thank God.
Shut the door, they're following me.
They're right behind me.
- Hey, calm down.
[Limping Man] Shut the door
before it's too late, man.
(ferocious growling)
What the, what is that?
(grunting)
(growling)
(intense music)