(dramatic music)
(explosion booming)
(glass shattering)
(electricity zapping)
[Girl] Dad?
[Woman] It's okay, sweetie.
(heavy breathing)
[Radio] The Windpines
Ranch, this is Cabrillo High.
Do you copy?
AJ, do you copy?
Are you alive?
David, it's me.
We're all safe.
The bunker held up.
[David] That's good to hear.
So what do we do now?
Now we wait.
(electricity zapping)
Okay then.
Let's get out of here.
Are you sure about this?
No I'm not.
Dad!
What about Mr. Wilson?
We haven't heard from David in days.
Either his radio is down or--
He went outside too.
You guys get your mask on.
It's time.
(heavy breathing)
(wind whistling)
(shouting)
(groaning)
Dad, watch out!
Apple, gun!
Back off tough guy.
Are you fucking deaf?
I will kill you.
(gun fires)
(groaning)
David?
No one's killing anyone.
We got way worse things out here
to worry about than each other.