-Previously onThis Is Us...
-How was football?
Coach said we've got another
Terry Bradshaw right here.
Minus the hair loss.
Ten...
You really think
it's okay for Kev
to be pumping iron?
-Hey, I got this.
-I think I just got the part.
I mean, pending a-a good meeting
with the director,
:
I-I got the part.
I have a strong feeling
about you guys.
I'Őm never leaving this bed.
You cannot make me.
I think I got...
maybe two hours of sleep?
What? You got two whole hours?
-Who are you?
I'Őm so tired, I can't even
remember the name of the guy
from the fairy tale,
the one who sleeps for too long.
Something...
Something Von Something?
Hey, we-we can'Őt
keep doing this.
Miguel and Shelly said
we just got to let Kevin
cry himself to sleep.
I know, I know, I know.
Maybe we just, maybe we just
give it one more night?
Babe, we'Őve been saying that
for months.
Look, how is Kevin gonna
teach himself to sleep
if every time he cries, we're
just, we're rushing in there
-to pick him up?
-Rip Van Winkle.
Rip Van Winkle, that's the name
of the guy from the fairy tale
-I couldn't remember.
-Babe?
-What?
-Tonight'Ős the night.
Tonight we let him cry it out.
Okay?
Okay. Tonight'Ős the night.
Hmm.
I got it. I got it.
You stay and take a nap.
Kevin is going
to literally explode.
Coach says to bulk up,
I have to eat 50 eggs a week.
"Nobody can eat 50 eggs."
Cool Hand Luke?
Only one of the greatest movies
of all-- Tough room.
Tough room.
-You okay, Kev?
Yeah, I...
woke up early
to work out with Dad,
and I was up late
memorizing the playbook.
Okay, well,
just don'Őt push it, bud.
When I have to memorize stuff
for a test,
I use rainbow flash cards.
The different colors help your
brain retrieve the information.
Ah, that'Ős really cool.
-It is?
-No, you dork.
It'Ős totally lame,
like everything else you do.
Kev, don'Őt knock it, all right?
That is a straight-A system
that Randall'Ős got right there.
All right, school time.
Let's go, guys.
Finish up.
Get your book bags, okay?
-Let's go.
Can you grab him...?
Yeah, no, I got it. Kev,
I'm gonna pick you up
after football today.
Wait. Lunches, Kev.
Randall, Bug.
Thanks.
-Jack.
-Yeah.
Kevin is totally exhausted.
Of course he'Ős exhausted.
He'Ős working hard
at something that he loves.
Babe, it's-it's the best kind
of exhausted.
See you in a bit.
-Kevin.
Ava.
-Oh, my God, hi.
-Hi.
It's so good to finally meet you
in person. This is great.
I got to tell you,
I'Őm beyond thrilled to finally
-get to work with you.
-Thank you. Me, too.
You know what? I'm a little
nervous to meet Foster.
I-- his last film, right?
I-I thought it was the greatest
thing I'd seen all year.
Me, too. I'Őm obsessed.
-I'Őve seen it
at least ten times.
-Right?
I have to ask,
are we supposed to call him
Jordan Martin Foster
or just Foster?
I have no-- I-I'Őve heard both.
-Yeah.
-I don't know what he likes.
We'll just feel it out, I guess.
-We'll find out.
Hey, guys.
-Hey.
-Thank you for doing
all the quarantining
and testing.
-Oh, I'll text you
when we're done.
Okay, thanks.
-See you later.
Thank you.
Ava.
-Hi.
-Oh, my God.
I am so glad that you agreed
to do this film.
I told the producer,
I said, "If Ava says no,
"I'Őm not doing it either,
'cause there would literally
be no point."
Oh, my God,
ten pages into the script,
I called my agent and I was
like, "I have to do this film.
I have to."
-So, thank you.
Yeah, I just...
I feel the same way.
You know? After your first film,
I thought, you know, any role
this guy wants me to play,
I will do it, let alone
a character like this.
You know, so complex, right?
-Unpredictable in a movie...
-Film.
Uh, it'Ős a film.
Anyway,
let'Ős dig into the script,
shall we?
Uh, I would like to start
with the two-hander scene
between you guys,
starting on page eight.
-Are you sure?
-I'Őm sure.
'Cause once we sign
these papers...
Babe, it'Ős a birth plan,
it's not a deal with the devil.
Okay? Either party
can change their mind
-at any time.
-Yeah, don'Őt remind me.
We are totally
at Ellie'Ős mercy here,
until the baby is born.
Even after the baby is born,
we are at Ellie's mercy.
Until she signs
the relinquishment papers,
we are completely at Ellie'Ős...
-mercy.
-Mercy. I know. I know, Tobe.
Well, Ellie is going
to her ob-gyn appointment today
and only one person can go,
and she asked me to come,
so, I don't know, that'Ős got
to be a-a good sign, right?
Yes. Yes.
Why do we call it an ob-gyn?
We don'Őt call
a cardiologist a C-A-R-D
or a dermatologist a D-E-R-M.
Okay, uh, will Serious Toby
be watching the ultrasound
on FaceTime?
Or will Funny Toby miss seeing
Baby Chloe for the first time?
Baby Chloe?
So, have we decided
to go with that name?
I think we have.
Serious Toby is very excited.
It'Ős just hard to tell
because he'Ős so serious.
Okay.
Mother, can we please go
to the salon today?
-My hair is a fright.
A fright?
Mom, I told you not to let her
watch Little Womenagain.
Okay. Politician'Ős dilemma:
solid versus striped.
Solid says I stand
by my convictions.
Hmm. Striped says I represent
my entire community.
It'Ős very cute, you want
to look nice for your protŽgŽ.
Honey, I prefer to think of him
as my apprentice.
Thank you.
Hey, Dej.
Big day today.
Of all the people that Malik
could have asked to shadow
at work for his school project,
who did he choose?
Hint: his name rhymes
with Gandall Gearson,
and he'Ős your gather...
It'Ős a civics assignment,
and you'Őre the only city
councilman in his COVID pod.
-Who else is he gonna ask?
-Your father and your boyfriend
spending
the entire day together.
-What could go wrong?
You'Őre enjoying this
way too much.
Something is wrong with you.
Hey, Malik.
Hey, Mrs. Pearson.
-Nice suit.
-Thank you.
Ooh.
8:06.
Thought we said 8:00 sharp.
-Oh. I-I'Őm sorry,
Mr. Pearson. I'm...
-I'Őm just messing with you, man.
Striped. It's a good call.
And, look, thank you again
for letting me do this.
You know, I'Őve lived
in Philly my whole life,
so I am excited to see
how the city runs.
Malik, it'Ős my pleasure.
It's my pleasure.
Okay, a couple things.
-Mm-hmm?
Don'Őt talk about us, okay?
Don'Őt talk about me.
Don'Őt talk about you.
Actually,
just don'Őt talk at all.
And good luck or whatever.
You look good in that suit.
Okay, we are now officially
seven minutes behind schedule.
That is seven minutes of
problems that don'Őt get solved
because you were late, Malik.
Let'Ős not make it eight.
Hey, yo, yo, yo.
Gandall Gearson gout.
:
Kate and Randall are down.
Yeah. Kevin, too, finally.
He fell asleep in my arms
and then I managed
to slide him into his crib
without waking him up.
-It was a real pro move.
-Such a pro move.
-Yeah.
-Oof.
Yeah, I should make sure
that he's in an okay position.
No, babe, babe, babe, come on.
W-We agreed we got to give him
a chance to calm himself down.
-He'Őll stop.
-He'll stop.
How was practice?
Fine.
Hey, hey.
-Oh, hey, Coach.
-Hey.
-How you doing?
It's good to see you.
-Good to see you.
-Yeah.
Hey, I, wanted to, uh,
I wanted to clear something up.
I didn'Őt expect the
boys to actually eat 50 eggs.
It'Ős a line from a movie.
Well, it sounds like
what we'Őve got here
is a failure to communicate.
Ah. Clearly a man
who knows his movies.
Yeah.
We did have some bumps
on the field today.
-Kevin hasn'Őt got
the playbook down.
-Really?
Well, he-he'Ős been
studying real hard.
Well, to be honest,
Kev'Ős probably not
my biggest fan
right now, eh, Kevin?
I was riding him
pretty hard out there today.
He'Ős got something special,
no doubt,
but he'Ős got to be willing
to put in the work.
I have kids with half his talent
running drills
seven days a week.
My son is up for it.
Glad to hear it.
Allegheny College
has a weekend QB camp
for seventh and eighth graders
right up in Meadville.
Kev would be a great fit.
But if I'Őm gonna recommend him
for a spot...
-He's got to put the work in.
-He needs to earn it. Yes, sir.
He will. Right, Kevin?
-Right.
Thanks, Jack.
Yeah.
-I'll see you later, sport.
You got yourself
into some trouble.
I didn'Őt get myself
into anything.
Okay. Why'd they call me?
To be honest, I have no idea.
-"To be honest"?
-Yeah.
Here's the thing,
when somebody says
"To be honest" or
"If I'Őm being honest with you"
or "Honestly,"
it usually means they'Őre
about ready to lie to you.
Okay, let's, let'Ős hold there,
for a second.
Ava, excellent.
You are giving him
as little as possible,
but you'Őre giving me
everything that I need.
And... okay.
Let'Ős just take it back
to the top of the scene.
Okay.
Yeah. Sure, okay.
Got yourself into some trouble.
I didn'Őt get myself
into anything.
So why'd they call me?
To be honest, I have no idea.
-"To be honest."
-Yeah.
Hang-hang, hang on.
-Kevin.
-Uh-huh?
Just, just take it back
a couple lines.
Sure. Sure.
So why'd they call me?
-To be honest, I have no idea.
-"To be honest."
Yeah.
-One more time?
Then why'd they call me?
To be honest,
I have no idea.
-"To be honest"?
-Can I get that last line again?
-You know, I just-- if you want
to give me a specific detail...
No, no. Stay in the scene,
please stay...
I'Őm trying to stay in the scene,
but you keep... interrupting me.
Believe me, Kevin, I wish
I didn'Őt have to interrupt.
:
Good to... All right.
All right.
Um, just from the same...
s... pickup.
Um...
We'Őre hearing from a lot
of renters about evictions,
but we'Őre also getting a lot
of complaints from landlords
-about delinquent rents.
Yeah.
Let'Ős finalize the language
on our motion
and get it to the council.
All right.
We keeping you up, Malik?
No. Sorry.
Oh, unfortunately,
I won't be able to shoot
your livestream today.
I'Őve got a budget meeting
at the same time.
All right. We livestream
a daily community bulletin.
I cover local news and answer
questions from constituents.
Oh, yeah, I know. That's
the one Deja watches every day.
She watches every day?
I am a dead man
-for telling you that.
-Oh, definitely.
Better call your lawyer
and draw up a will.
Hey, Malik.
How would you like to cover
the bulletin today?
Me?
-Yeah.
You'Őre one of the more capable
young humans I'Őve met.
We'Őll set you up at a desk
outside and you just have
to make sure the livestream
starts and ends on cue.
-Sound good?
Uh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
-For sure. I'Őm on it.
Thank you, Malik.
Uh, let'Ős just make sure
to get a camera angle
that doesn't go
right up his nose.
I don'Őt need to be reminded,
Jae-won.
I read all the comments.
Never read the comments!
This probably sounds insane,
but did you ever wonder
what the ultrasound jelly
tastes like?
Yes.
Every time that we'Őre here.
I know.
Oh, uh, speaking of eating,
Ellie, do you think you maybe
want to have lunch with me
after this?
Yeah, I'Őd love to.
Okay.
Here she is.
Looking great.
Heartbeat is strong.
There she is.
There'Ős Chloe.
-Well, it's a good thing
-Randall and Kate
are such heavy sleepers, huh?
This-this-this isn'Őt
normal crying, Jack.
He'Ős never cried
like this before.
Maybe something'Ős wrong.
Maybe he'Ős hurt.
Miguel and Shelly said he's...
Enough with Miguel and Shelly.
Who made them experts, anyway?
Their kids are train wrecks!
What's so funny?
That'Ős, that's the sound
of our son
being emotionally traumatized
for life.
Rebecca, do you remember
this morning when we said,
"Tonight'Ős the night"?
We held hands and...
Yeah, I-I don'Őt care
what I said this morning,
because I didn'Őt know then
that he'Őd be crying
like a maniac for a half hour.
It'Ős been six minutes.
-No way.
-Mm-hmm.
-What?
-Look, I know this hurts.
I know it hurts, babe,
but, but don'Őt you want him
to show that crib who'Ős boss?
No. I don'Őt care.
I'm sorry,
I have to go in there.
-Hi.
Hey.
Is everything all right?
Yeah, just a few bumps
at practice.
But we'Őll run some drills
after dinner,
I'll find the problems.
I just got home
from practice, Dad.
It'Ős fine, Kev,
you can take the night off.
No, he can'Őt, okay?
The coach said the other kids...
I don'Őt care what Coach says.
I'Őm gonna quit.
-No.
Kev, you'Őre not gonna quit.
All right?
You'Őre the quarterback.
You made a commitment
to that team.
You don't just quit the second
something starts to feel tough.
Okay?
I'm tired.
-You should have talked to me
before making a decision
like that.
Wh-- You seriously want
to let him quit?
After h-having one rough day?
He'Ős clearly miserable, okay?
I'm-I'Őm gonna go up there
and tell him if he doesn't want
to play anymore,
he doesn'Őt have to.
Rebecca, I'Őm strongly asking you
not to do that.
You about ready?
I want to squeeze in
a quick jog after this.
-Yeah, it's looking like
we're good to go.
-Great.
I will count you down
to start the livestream.
And you just let the bulletin
play until you hear me say...
: "Thank you
for your time, Philadelphia.
We'Őll talk again tomorrow."
Just get the hell
out of here, man.
These are trucks
that can drive right in
and set up safe,
clean testing sites...
Dad's doing his bulletin.
Uh, we're trying
different spots around town,
so check my website
for an updated list.
Food banks are starting
to see...
-...bumps in need
as the weather changes.
Donations are always
appreciated.
But please know
that everyone in this office
is working to make sure  that nobody in our community...
Hey, Mom,
I'Őm still at city hall.
-I read every message...
Uh, no, no, she-she was fine
this morning.
I know that folks
are struggling right now.
Look, I-I left a teething ring
in the freezer.
At a time when my birth father
didn'Őt have a family,
this community was his family.
When I'm having
a hard day at work
or get frustrated that things
aren'Őt moving fast enough,
I remind myself
that I am doing this for him.
I'Őm doing this for William Hill.
Because you all were his family.
Which means
that you'Őre my family, too.
I'm not gonna cry today.
I know a lot of you like
to take bets on that, so...
Thanks for your time,
Philadelphia.
We'Őll talk again tomorrow.
All right.
-Yeah, no, okay. Listen, um...
Malik,
I'm gonna change
-and go for that run.
-If she starts crying again,
just give her some baby Tylenol.
But remember to check
the dosage, please.
I know you know.
Uh, Beth?
Hold on, hon, I'Őm just
in the middle of something.
Uh, o-okay, but Randall'Ős
taking his clothes off
in front of the whole city
of Philadelphia.
Mom? Dad's getting naked!
What?
Oh, my G--
Tess, call your father.
He'Ős not answering.
Of course he can'Őt see
his phone,
he's too busy... dancing.
Mm-mm, girl, that'Ős not dancing.
I don'Őt know what that is,
but that is not dancing.
Mom, I want to watch.
Hey, hey, hey.
Annie, you know what?
There's some things
you can'Őt unsee, baby,
and this is one of them,
all right?
All right, all right, bye.
Love you.
Hey, Dej, what's up?
Sh...
I know.
I know. I just, I-I think
he needed to know
that he wasn't alone.
-That's all.
He is a child.
He is a child playing a game.
It'Ős supposed to be fun.
-Here we go.
-Here we go what?
You'Őve been doing this to him
his entire life.
The second he starts to complain
about something being too hard,
you let him off the hook.
Excuse me?
Guitar lessons, uh, Boy Scouts.
Oh, I'm sorry,
our-our six-year-old got tired
of tying knots all day,
so I let him bail on Boy Scouts.
Put me in mom jail.
You just, you can be
really easy on him.
And it'Ős made him a little...
What? It's made him what?
Soft.
It's made him soft.
Hey, nerd, tell me how your
stupid rainbow system works.
Very funny.
But whatever the trick is,
I'Őm not falling for it.
For real.
I need your help.
I keep messing up the plays.
Please?
Hey, Foster.
Or, uh, Jordan Martin Foster
or JMF?
I don't know what-- I don't know
what you...
I don't know
what you want to be called.
Is that what
you waited around to ask me?
No. No. I-I, um...
: Uh, you were
pretty rough on me in there.
You know? And I was, I was
just wondering if you had
any specific feedback for me
so that I could, you know...
I want to give you
what you want, in the scene.
I didn't realize
you were the kind of guy
that needs an attaboy.
-No, no, it's...
-Look, look, today
I learned that
you are a good actor.
And there's nothing wrong
with being a good actor.
And when you die,
people will say,
"Oh, yeah, I remember him.
He was good."
Or you could be
one of the greats.
Now, here's the good news,
Kevin: you get to decide.
Is today as close as you get
to greatness...
or do you come back tomorrow?
See you tomorrow.
Hey.
Okay, I'm really, really scared
that I tanked it in there
when I called the baby Chloe.
It was totally insensitive.
You know, I can't even imagine
the thousands of emotions
that you're feeling,
and then I go naming her and...
But, Ellie, are you...
are you having second thoughts?
Look, it...
caught me by surprise.
The name.
This is all a lot for me.
Yeah, of course it is.
Kate, I told you
that my husband died.
We met in tenth grade.
But it took him a long time
to ask me out.
And even when he did,
it was going... slow.
We barely kissed.
So, one day we go to the beach,
and I decide, you know what,
I'm just gonna take charge.
And I pull my T-shirt off,
and I'm standing there
in my cute bikini top, and he
is just staring at my chest,
like, confused, and he's like,
"Wait, you don't have a big
hairy birthmark on your chest
in the shape of South America?"
What?
All year, his bio lab partner
had been telling him
these crazy stories about me.
And the lab partner...
her name was Chloe Penner.
:
No.
Yeah.
So look, you...
you deserve to name this baby
whatever you want.
-But does it have to be Chloe?
One time.
I went out just one time...
two years after Doug died.
A few months ago, I...
decided that
I couldn't have this baby,
and I made an appointment
to have an abortion.
And I got as far as
the parking lot at the clinic.
And I know that some people
have very strong feelings
-about...
-I'm not judging you at all.
For me...
that wasn't the right choice.
:
Yeah.
So, am I having second thoughts?
About pretty much
my entire life.
Except this.
Except you and Toby.
About that I am sure.
Hundred percent sure, Kate.
Mr. Pearson, I am so...
I am so sorry.
I'm sure at your age...
city hall's a bit boring.
But you asked
to shadow me, Malik.
The work we do here is serious.
I expected you
to take it seriously.
Not show up late,
yawn your way through it,
and forget to do
the most important part
of the one thing
I asked you to do.
I know. I-I messed up.
I did.
But...
Mr. Pearson, do you know what
time I had to be up this morning
to get to your place
only six minutes late?
4:30.
I usually get up at 5:00,
so that I can make sure
that I prepare all
of Janelle's meals for the day,
do her laundry,
wash all her bottles,
all before she gets up at 6:00.
Today I had to pack a lunch
and iron my shirt, so 4:30.
This stuff is not boring at all.
But I have a daughter.
What she needs...
it always comes first.
Even if that means making the
things that I want for myself
that much harder.
I was 17 when I lost my father.
And I felt like I owed it
to my family
to make my dreams smaller.
More practical.
But I was wrong.
Listen to me when I say this.
Do not make your dreams smaller.
Make 'em bigger.
Not in spite of your daughter.
Forher.
Uh...
I-I appreciate that,
Mr. Pearson.
I don't think
the size of my dreams
need to be worried about,
though.
I get straight A's.
I'm going to go
to an Ivy League college
and major in business.
Then I'm gonna go
to culinary school,
so that I can open up
the first restaurant
in Philadelphia history
to get three Michelin stars.
Well, damn. Okay.
Seems like your dreams are of
the perfectly appropriate size.
Wh-What I do need, though,
is a killer internship
for these college applications.
I was thinking maybe city hall?
I think that can be arranged.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
You-you know Deja's gonna lose
her mind, right?
-Oh, I'm counting on it, bruh.
-No, no, no.
Out of my way, Jack.
-Can't do that.
What we're doing isn't working.
I can't move from this door,
as much as I want to.
Just...
a little longer.
All right, you ready?
Yeah.
-Uh, same ones?
-Same ones.
Um, pro-right split,
897 F motion right...
-option zone?
-You got it!
-That's ten in a row.
-Yes.
-Okay, let's do ten more.
-Okay.
-Hey, Kev.
Well, I had the worst first day with this new director.
I feel like he put me in a bag
and just beat me
with a baseball bat.
Why would he put you in a bag?
Why wouldn't he beat you up
outside of the bag?
No, because when
you're in the bag,
you don't know where
he's hitting you.
You know, just random spots
all over the body.
So you don't know where
the next blow's gonna land.
Oof.
I mean, are you sure working
with him is even worth it?
Um, I don't know, maybe,
uh, I...
I've been thinking a lot
about Mom, you know?
She's-she's stuck out there
at that cabin.
She's using her phone
to stay connected to the family,
and I just thought...
how nice it would be
to do something really great.
Like take her to the Oscars.
Or, like, to win an Oscar,
and then I could stand up
in front of everyone
and just thank her
for everything she did for me.
I'd like to do that while she
can still remember, you know?
First I got to give a
performance that's not so tired.
Kev.
Hmm?
Kate, come on, I'm too tired
for subtext. Just tell me.
Your big fight with Randall--
I mean, didn't he say
that your acting was tired?
This has nothing to do
with Randall, Kate, all right?
This has...
nothing to do with him.
You know, I had a...
conversation with him
on, um, our birthday.
And he said some things
that I just can't stop
thinking about.
You know, ab-about
what it was like...
as a black kid
growing up in our family
with white parents,
you know,
and-and white siblings and...
how it must have felt for him,
and how unseen...
-he felt.
-Unseen?
Kate, Mom and Dad
were obsessed with Randall.
All right? All we tried to do is
get five minutes a day with them
when they weren't paying
attention to Randall.
Kev...
we don't even talk to him
about this stuff, though.
You know? And we don'Őt talk
to him about what it was like
or-or what it's still like
for him.
Okay.
Look, I'm not an idiot, okay?
I...
I understand it probably wasn't
a walk in the park
to be the only black kid
in that fancy private school
he went to.
But let's not sit here
and pretend
that Mom and Dad
did anything wrong, okay?
I'm just saying,
we all have stuff
from our past that we're
still dealing with, okay?
And that's Randall, you andme.
What does that mean?
Nothing.
Honestly, I'm just tired.
It's been a really long day.
Honestly?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Hey, baby.
Hey.
Yeah. I'm not...
I'm not ready
to laugh about it yet.
Oh, no, not yet?
No.
Okay, will you let me know
when you are?
Because, um,
I have so much laughter
on the inside of me, I just...
would like to get that out.
Appreciate it.
Malik told me
about the internship.
You're ruining my life.
You know that, right?
I do.
Thank you.
You gonna give that boy
an internship
after what he did today?
Look, after what happened today,
that kid will not allow himself
to screw up again.
Trust me. I was that kid.
All right. As long as
his parents don't have
-to come over for dinner.
Excuse me.
What up, Jae-won?
Someone posted it.
Today's, uh, bulletin.
And it's kind of going viral.
Well, viral how?
Your bulletins
usually get 5,000 views.
This one
is already over 100,000.
It might make the news tonight.
And not just the local stations, either.
Well, on the plus side,
the camera angle's
very flattering.
You know, these ultrasounds,
they look like somebody
made a baby out of wax
and then left it out
in the sun too long.
But I think...
I think I love
this melted wax baby.
Whatever her name will be.
What's up?
I thought you'd be excited
knowing that Ellie
is fully on board.
I'm fine.
Actually, I'm not fine at all.
Um, my talk with Ellie today
brought up some stuff for me.
Some stuff that I never wanted
to tell anyone.
I mean, not my mom.
Not my brothers.
And not you.
When I was 18,
I was in a really,
really bad relationship.
And when it ended...
Come in.
Are you sure
you don't want to come with us
-to New York?
-Yep.
Molly's gonna come over,
and we're gonna hang out
and make fun of Dawson's Creek.
Have fun.
-And tell Kevin I said congrats.
-All right.
-Love you.
-Bye, sweetheart.
-Bye.
Okay. Maybe you were right.
Maybe I am a little easy
on Kevin.
Really? What changed?
Well, I just went upstairs
to talk to him,
and he was with Randall,
who is helping him
memorize his playbook.
Jack, they high-fived.
It's just...
it's so hard for me to push them
when they seem unhappy.
You know, my-my dad
had a nickname for me
-when I was a kid?
-Uh-uh.
Jack of All Trades.
-Hmm.
-I mean, I-I thought
that sounded so cool.
You know, I-I thought that
that meant my dad thought
I was great at everything.
So, one day,
I decide to try and fix
the leaky kitchen faucet,
and I just couldn't do it.
I couldn't figure it out.
And Stanley...
He sneers at me,
and he says,
"Jack of All Trades,
Master of None."
And that's when I got it.
The whole time, he'd been saying
I was great
at absolutely nothing.
-Oh, Jack.
-No, it-it's fine.
I'm an ordinary man.
And for me,
the way my dad treated me,
to get out of that house
an ordinary man,
that is an accomplishment
in my book.
But...
Our kids,
I want them
to know their dad
sees greatness in them.
I will kill myself
to make them feel that way.
Even when...
Even when deep down,
I just want to hold my kid
and-and tell him
to go take a nap.
-Hey.
I feel sorry for your dad.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
To have had a son like you
and to have not seen
what was right in front of him.
Yeah.
You really saw them high-five?
Oh, yeah.
You sure they weren't just,
like,
trying to smack each other
in the face?
-Like, at the same time?
-: No.
You really do this
every time you take a test?
That must take forever.
It does. But being me
at my school,
I have to be the best.
-When I'm having
a hard day at work
or, uh, get frustrated
that things
aren't moving fast enough,
I remind myself
that I'm doing this for him.
I'm doing this for William Hill.
-...I'm doing this for him.
Because you all were his family.
Which means
you're my family, too.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH