♪ Shadows are falling ♪
♪ And I'm running
out of breath ♪
♪ Keep me in your heart
for a while ♪
♪ If I leave you,
it doesn't mean ♪
♪ I love you any less ♪
♪ Keep me in your heart
for a while ♪
♪ When you get up
in the morning ♪
♪ And you see that crazy sun ♪
♪ Keep me in... ♪
No. I still haven't heard
anything.
I'm really trying
not to freak out, Tobe.
♪ There's a train leaving... ♪
Wait, someone's at the door.
No, it's just Kevin and Madison.
Oh, well, hello to you, too.
Um, will you just keep looking?
Just... I'll call you
if I hear anything.
Okay.
- What's up?
- Oh, God.
Mom went to get a birthday cake,
and she hasn't come back.
I tried calling her.
She's not answering.
So, Toby went to the bakery,
and apparently,
she didn't even make it there.
- Oh, my God.
- Okay. I-I'm-I'm gonna go...
I'm gonna go look for her.
I'm gonna go help.
- Uh, are you okay?
- Yeah.
- No, yeah, go.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- Wait, what's going on?
Uh, no, nothing.
I had a little morning sickness,
- but...
- Oh, thank God. Um...
Yes.
Yes. Of course.
Um, thank you very much.
Yeah, we're here.
Okay.
S-So, the cops have her.
She, uh... She had an episode.
They're bringing her back here.
Let's all just, um...
Let's just stay calm.
We don't know what kind of state
she's gonna be in,
and-and I don't want
to panic her.
All right, ma'am, you're home.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Mom, come on in.
- Hi.
Thank you very much
for bringing her home.
Okay, thanks.
Oh, how's she doing back there?
Uh, she's laying down.
She's a little nauseous.
My fiancée's
got morning sickness
at all hours of the day.
Oh. Try ginger tea.
- Hey.
- Madison okay?
Yeah. Yeah, she's okay.
- Did you hear anything from Mom's doctor?
- No.
Miguel left her a message.
Kev, she was...
she was gone.
Like, like,
her face was not her face.
I know.
It's too soon.
I'm not ready for this.
Yeah, me neither.
Obviously, at some point,
you're gonna need to explain
your use of the word "fiancée."
Yeah, it's a long story.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Well, it's a long car ride home.
True that. Yeah.
Okay, so, Kev,
I tried calling you
for, like, two hours,
and you weren't answering.
I'm sorry.
"THIS IS US"
Season 05  Episode 02
Episode Title: "Forty Part 2"
I didn't...
I didn't know you were, uh...
Yeah.
- Hey.
Hi.
Hey.
I was just gonna call you
about Mom.
The cops found her.
They brought her home,
so she's-she's here.
She's safe.
She's-she's resting, so...
Well, I wish I could give you
a massive hug,
- but I don't know when you were...
- I'm-I'm good.
I get COVID tested
three times a week at city hall.
Plus Beth's turned into Fauci
at home, so...
You guys?
Yeah, we're g...
We, um, we quarantined
for 20 days before we got here,
so we're all good. -
Okay.
I want to see her.
- She upstairs? - Yeah.
- Yeah.
Randall.
There's no way we could've known
this was gonna happen.
She was great before this.
You can ask Kate.
I'm not questioning you, Kev.
I believe you.
She's home,
and that's what matters.
It's cool.
Cool.
Oh, hey...
Thank you for coming.
I know the last thing
that you need right now is
a terrified, panicked text
from your sister.
Randall.
- What...
- Hey.
Sweetheart, I thought...
I thought you weren't
gonna make it.
What, you think I'd miss
our birthday?
Oh...
You know.
- Kate called me.
- Mm.
Are Beth and the girls
with you?
No, they're back home.
Next time.
I'm clear. Kev said
you are, too.
I just want to be vigilant.
- Sit.
- Oh.
You want to tell me
what happened?
Mm...
I, uh...
I don't even know what to say.
Um, I went into town...
...and then the next thing
I knew...
William was there.
I mean, obviously not William,
but I...
Oh, God, I could have sworn
it was him.
I've been thinking about him
a lot lately.
Ever since we had our
conversation about the trial,
and about me, um...
keeping him from you.
We don't have to talk about that
right now, Mom. That's...
Well, then, when?
Hmm?
Wh-What's going on there?
Oh, that's just some poison ivy.
Miguel and I have been
gardening.
I already took something
for it.
Do you think this would have
happened in St. Louis?
I don't know.
- I'm sorry I pushed that on you.
- No.
No, no, no, sweetheart.
You have nothing
to apologize for.
Are Beth and the girls with you?
No, Mom.
- Uh, next time.
- Okay.
Hey, excuse me, excuse me, um...
My wife is Rebecca Pearson.
I don't have an update yet, sir.
Okay, wait, I-I don't...
I don't know what to do.
Um, what can I do?
You could pray.
Heh!
- What are you doing?
- Kevin, you need to talk to Randall.
Kev, I have tried my best
to stay out of this,
but now Randall's acting
all weird with me, too.
We haven't even done
our birthday chant,
and that's like canon.
- Oh, Kate, Kate...
- No, Kevin.
The world is on fire.
This is enough. Fix it.
Hey.
You know, after seeing
all those Internet videos
of random objects
that are actually cakes,
it's kind of a letdown
to have a cake that just...
looks like a cake.
You know...
...when Rebecca and I
first got here,
we thought we were gonna
be here for a week.
Two, max. Then that
turned into a month.
Then two months.
But...
she just kept feeling better.
And I... I'm not an idiot
or anything like that.
I know that
there's-there's no secret magic
in the air
that's gonna cure this,
but... she just seemed
like Rebecca again.
You know?
And now, with this...
Oh, man. It's just
gonna take the legs
right out from underneath her.
Okay, I'm gonna try
to say something meaningful
right now, Migs,
and I got to warn you,
it is gonna be a reach.
So, you just bear with me, okay?
Okay.
So every morning, I take 20
milligrams of an antidepressant.
Uh, I'm not sure who else
knows that besides Kate,
but it's-it's not a big deal.
So, about a month after
I started taking, uh, the meds,
I called my doctor
to renew my prescription.
And he said,
"Oh, no, don't worry about it.
You have automatic refills."
That hit me... really hard.
You know, it just made it feel
so indefinite,
so... so permanent.
I said,
"Is there ever gonna be a time
"when I am noton these meds?
I mean, is-is this ever
gonna end?"
And... and then he...
He says, "One day at time."
- Hmm.
- One day at a time.
An excellent TV show, and a
terrible answer to my question.
Now, I don't know how it feels
to stare down Alzheimer's.
But I do know how it feels
to look at your life
and to see all the things
that you want from it,
and to have them all seem
so unattainable.
Rebecca had a bad day.
She's gonna have more.
You know.
My long-winded advice is for you
to remind her that to you,
her happy future is very real.
One day at a time.
It's a great show.
The reboot is better.
I know.
I'm the one who started
the hashtag to get it revived
- after it got canceled.
- Is that right?
You don't cancel Rita Moreno.
Amen.
Yeah.
Oh, this is Rebecca's doctor
from L.A.
- Yeah, go ahead.
- I got to take this.
Hello. Hi, uh, Dr. Whitaker.
Is that her doctor?
I need to speak with her.
Yeah, yeah. This, uh...
It was this afternoon.
- Give me the...
- It was a very severe episode.
Miguel, I'd like to talk to her.
Randall, just hold on
one second, please. Uh...
Ask her if anything could have
- negatively interacted with her meds.
- Just...
Ask her
about the allergy medicine,
the one she took
for poison ivy. Here.
Are you sure she took this?
Yeah, she told me.
Hey, Dr. Whitaker, uh, yeah.
It looks like Rebecca took
an antihistamine with...
Yes, diphenhydramine.
I do remember it from the list.
Okay. Right.
So it could have been
a reaction to the...
Thank God. Okay.
Yes, she's resting right now.
Yes.
Absolutely. Yes, I will.
Please forgive me.
I'm so sorry.
She was in... so much pain.
Shh.
It's okay. Shh.
It's okay.
You've been crying all night.
Aren't you tired? Huh?
Still bad?
We should go to the clinic,
- try to get you looked at.
- No.
If I tell that doctor
I'm on methadone to get clean,
he'll look at me like I'm dirt.
Less than.
- Laurel, please.
- No!
I need you to get me
some stuff for the pain.
Please. I've been good.
I have.
It just... It hurts so bad.
I just need a little help.
Just need a little help.
Okay? Just one more time.
So I can be there for the baby.
I-I can't do it by myself.
I can't take care of him.
I'm so sorry.
Please be with him.
Please take care of him.
Excuse me.
He used to pray so hard
you could see the veins
in his neck.
Yeah, I remember that.
The veins in his neck.
Never knew what he was
asking for.
I used to tell myself
he was asking to be better.
Better to us.
A better man.
And then I would pray.
Pray that it would work.
That he would change.
Then, when he never did...
that's when I gave up
on all of this.
Every hand you've dealt me
has been crap.
But still, I kept trying.
All these years...
trying to always do
what's right.
Trying to be the better man;
the man that he never was.
Has that made you laugh...
seeing me try?
Knowing that,
somewhere deep down...
in spite of everything,
that I probably still believed.
The only good thing that has
ever happened to me is her,
and if you...
Please do not take her
away from me.
I am begging you.
I'm on my knees
begging for her.
Begging for my children.
Take me if you want,
just don't...
Just don't.
Don't you dare.
I had no idea that
medications could interact that way.
- And they're sure it's temporary?
- That's what the doctor said.
Said a reaction like that
can cause an episode
and then it can just wear off.
It was a hell of a catch,
Randall.
Back at you.
We're lucky you came, Randall.
- Honestly.
- Yeah.
I'm just happy she's okay.
So, um... I'm gonna take off.
Wait, what? Now?
- But cake.
- I, uh...
I promised Beth and the girls
that I'd get home tonight.
They got a whole thing planned,
so...
- Miguel.
- Drive safe.
Tobias.
Sis.
Kev.
Bye again.
Hey, Randall.
So, I was, uh... I was hoping
that you and Kev would talk,
you know?
- Clear the air.
- Kate...
I'm not taking any sides.
I know I live in L.A. with him,
but I am totally Switzerland
on this one.
Okay.
Randall.
Are we good?
I mean, I've been texting
and reaching out,
and I haven't heard
anything back, really, and...
I'm just so worried about...
about you and Beth
and the girls.
You know, with everything that's
going on in the news.
I'm so overwhelmed by it,
I can't even imagine
what you guys are all
going through, so..
I'm so sorry.
Sorry about what?
Specifically,
what are you apologizing for?
I'm just... I'm... sorry about
what's going on in the country
- and the protests and...
- Okay.
But you've never
apologized before.
And this isn't the first
Black person
to be killed on camera.
No, it's... it's not.
I don't know,
this feels different.
Not for me, Kate.
It-It's never been different
for me.
We grew up in the same house.
Things like this have been
happening to Black people
for years, and we've never
talked about it.
Not once.
Not once in 40 years.
I don't know what to say.
I don't want to say...
- I don't want to say the wrong thing.
- Okay.
So, growing up,
I, uh, I just had to keep
so many things to myself
because...
I didn't want to make
you guys feel bad.
I didn't want you to have
to worry about
saying the wrong thing.
Oh, God...
Well, you're right. I mean,
we never talked about it
as kids, and I think Mom and Dad
did the best they could,
I guess, but...
but I didn't get involved,
I-I didn't even...
See, I hate this, Kate.
I hate seeing you upset.
And normally I would hug you,
and I would tell you that
you did all the right things.
I would try to make it all
okay for you.
But if I did that, Kate...
If I made things better for you,
then where does that leave me?
I'm sorry, but I can't do that.
That has been my pattern
all my life.
And honestly, Kate,
it is exhausting.
I'm exhausted.
And all I want to do right now
is go home and be with my wife
and my girls.
Okay.
Okay, um...
I love you.
I love you, too.
Happy birthday, Sis.
Happy birthday.
Yeah?
It's Jack.
Been a while.
Yeah.
You okay?
Yeah. I...
No, I...
I don't know.
Can I ask you something?
What were you praying for?
I mean, you know,
back when we used
to go to church.
You need money again
or something?
Wh-What's going on?
No, I'm good.
I don't know why I called.
I was just... having a day.
Uh... I'll let you go.
- I hope you're okay.
- Jack.
Yeah?
Uh, I prayed my kids would
turn out better than I did.
I'm trying, Pop.
I'm really trying.
Yeah, I-I know.
- I gotta go.
- Hey, Jackie?
Yeah?
Happy birthday, kid.
♪ I been down this road before ♪
♪ I remember every tree... ♪
Thanks, Pop.
♪ Every single blade of grass ♪
♪ Holds a special place for me ♪
♪ And I remember every town ♪
♪ And every hotel room ♪
♪ Every song I ever sang ♪
♪ On a guitar out of tune ♪
♪ I remember everything ♪
♪ Things I can't forget ♪
♪ The way you turned
and smiled on me... ♪
And he wound up here.
Exact same place,
exact same day.
♪ Your ocean eyes of blue... ♪
Just look at him, Bec.
Placed right there.
Right next to ours.
♪ Like roses miss the dew. ♪
Hey, Randall.
Hey, listen,
I just wanted to, uh...
Just wanted to say thanks
for, uh...
thanks for coming out, you know,
I really appreciate it.
If you hadn't, we, uh...
No. Yeah, of course.
Yeah.
- I should go to beat the traffic.
- Yeah.
Hey, Randall, uh...
I'm having a-a girl.
A girl and a boy.
We just found out.
Congratulations, Kev.
That's great news.
Thanks.
Yeah, you're the first person
I've told.
And I feel like, I don't know,
I feel like the boy,
you know, I was a boy once,
I can handle a boy, right?
But the girl, I...
Ooh! So...
Anyway, you got any
advice for me?
You'll let her get away
with anything.
But her mom will be there
to fix your mistakes.
Mom will probably be better
at everything, honestly.
Yeah.
Yeah, she probably will be.
You know, in the strangest
of ways...
I feel like I might have...
really found someone
really special, you know?
I gotta go.
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday, Randall.
You gonna keep staring at me,
or you gonna tell me
your name?
I don't know.
You gonna tell me your name?
- I'm Laurel.
- William.
But around here they call me...
Shakespeare!
Shakespeare, it's your stop.
You're home, kid.
You getting off or what?
No, I'm not getting off.
So just... keep going.
Hi, Randall.
Hi, Dr. Leigh.
Uh, sorry to bother you.
I hope it's an okay time to...
No, of course.
I-I saw your name,
and I wanted to make sure
everything was all right.
Yeah, no,
everything's all right.
But...
When we first met, Dr. Leigh,
you made a point of pointing out
just how few Black men
seek you out for therapy.
It's a "very small number,"
were your words.
I remember.
I made a conscious choice
to start seeing
a white female therapist.
I know that.
It's complicated for me,
and I can't claim
to understand it,
but I... but I do know it.
If that makes sense.
There are things, Dr. Leigh,
that I don't feel comfortable
talking to you about.
There's stuff I-I put away
when I enter your office, and...
that doesn't help me get better.
And there's nothing you can do
to make me more comfortable.
I just...
I need something different.
I'm gonna make a change
and find a Black therapist.
And I just wanted
to tell you that directly.
Randall, obviously your mental
health is what's important her,
and if that's something that
you're feeling strongly about..
Hey.
I knew that the meal
was important to you, so...
I'm doing the best
that I can.
So be gentle in your critique.
Is that what
it's gonna feel like...
when I eventually...
We don't have to worry
about that.
Not-not today.
- You know what's so strange?
- Hmm?
I'm not worried about
forgetting about the big stuff.
It's the little things.
It's the...
It's the regular...
Saturday when the kids
were little.
A day when nothing big
really happens. J...
We were just there,
a normal family,
like any other normal family.
Laughing and talking and...
...playing pin the tail
on the donkey.
That's the stuff I'm not ready
to let go of yet.
I want to show you something.
Come on.
- Come on.
- What...
- I chopped down the dead tree.
- Hmm.
And I know that you said
you wanted to plant a sapling...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...so that we could get fruit sooner, but,
I don't know, it just seemed,
um... too easy.
So, instead, I got these.
Oh...
Now, these should bear fruit
in about... six to ten years.
Six to ten years?
I don't...
I am not in a rush.
One day at a time.
And then another...
And then another.
I love you.
- I love you.
- Thank you.
Hey.
Guess what.
What's going on?
I can't stop thinking about
what Randall said.
I've been so oblivious.
- What can I do?
- Noth-Nothing.
That's sweet,
but I'm gonna have to
sit with these feelings
a while.
Well, we'll just have to get it
all right raising our children.
Yeah. Yes.
Raising our children,
- which is the plural of "child."
- Mm-hmm.
Children.
Are you doing something
confusing?
'Cause I don't...
I don't get it.
Apparently. Listen.
I just got six messages
from the adoption agency.
Kate, we have a match.
Wh...
What?
They found us a match.
- For real?
- Yes.
- We're getting a baby?
- We gettin' a ba...
♪ I don't think you want
grand gestures ♪
♪ Just a simple
faithful friend ♪
♪ Someone who will
walk it with you ♪
♪ All the way to the end ♪
♪ Someone who can live
and love you ♪
♪ Singing how I've come
to know ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ You're like the sun
that gives ♪
♪ The moon its glow ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ You're my, oh, you are my ♪
♪ My sweet refuge ♪
♪ You're my... ♪
And another one.
Mmm.
♪ But we'll leave them
chasing tails ♪
♪ 'Cause you're my, oh,
you are my... ♪
I'm not having a breakdown,
Beth. I'm really not.
I'm healthier
than I've been in years.
But what I'm dealing
with at work,
and what we're dealing with
as a people,
day after day...
- It's just so tragic, Beth.
- Mm-hmm.
So much loss.
It's just so sad.
I-I'm not falling apart.
I'm not having a breakdown.
I'm just really,
really sad, baby.
When my dad was dying, I...
remember he said
that it's the tragedies
that define our lives.
"They are the fence posts
on which
the rest of our lives
hang, baby girl."
I always think about that.
Like...
our lives just hanging there,
between these really sad
fence posts.
Baby.
You were born out of tragedy.
♪ I need you, I need you... ♪
Multiple tragedies.
♪ Lord, every day,
I need you... ♪
All that loss, all that sadness.
♪ I need you, I need you... ♪
And look at what you've hung on
your fence posts.
Look right in front of you.
Right here in this room, and...
I mean, look what you did
with all of that.
Do you see it?
I see it.
You are a beautiful,
resilient man.
The world is a brilliant,
resilient place.
We fight on.
Darkest before dawn
and all that?
Sourest lemons
life has to offer.
Okay, that's your thing,
you know what I mean?
- I was doing my thing.
- Mm-hmm.
Can we stay with my thing?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
This pain is not forever.
This moment in time
is not forever.
Nothing is forever, except us.
- We fight on.
♪ I need you ♪
♪ You're my ♪
♪ Oh, you are my ♪
♪ My sweet refuge ♪
♪ You're my, oh, you are my... ♪
- Be honest with me.
- Hmm?
You're not, like,
secretly expecting
- some big surprise party or anything?
- Mm-mm, no.
All I need
is in this room right now.
I think we could all use
a year with no surprises.
Mm. Yes.
- Yeah.
- Mm.
Let's
mark the time and call it in.
We need to call the cops
and Child Services, too.
This is a mess.
Sir, we're gonna need you
to wait here.
Where'd he go?
I'll let the cops figure out
what to do about that.
Wait.
Wait. I think I've got a pulse.