P
Pr
Pre
Prev
Previ
Previo
Previou
Previous
Previousl
Previously
Previously O
Previously On
Previously On "
Previously On "T
Previously On "Th
Previously On "Thi
Previously On "This
Previously On "This I
Previously On "This Is
Previously On "This Is U
Previously On "This Is Us
Previously On "This Is Us.
Previously On "This Is Us..
Previously On "This Is Us...
Previously On "This Is Us..."
[RANDALL [over phone]]
How does it feel
to be the Pearson family's
newest dad?
Congrats, Papa Bear.
[KEVIN]
Thank you very much.
Giving you to Toby and Kate
is the hardest thing
I've ever done.
But it might just be
the best thing I'll ever do.
[quietly]
I'm your mom.
We lost one of the babies.
No, that's not true.
[sobs]
That's not true.
Welcome to Labor and Delivery.
I know many of you
have been looking forward
to this rotation.
This is the floor
where you encounter
a lot of crying,
screaming and tantrums.
[whispers]
You're not gonna even pretend
to be interested?
[scoffs]
It's babies.
It's not that complicated.
[laughs softly]
[DOCTOR] For most families,
we're the last stop until
they start the long drive home
with their new baby.
Or in her case, babies, plural.
[whispers]
I have to go. Cover for me.
[REBECCA [softly]]
Okay.
Ooh.
All right.
There's a messy one.
Whoa, Kev... Kevin's peeing.
We got a pee-er.
Oh, I got him. I got him.
I got him. I got him.
[chuckles] Good.
There you go, bud. Here.
[groans]
[JACK] Thank you.
Let me wipe off...
[JACK]
You have one more?
[NURSE]
Well, look at you guys.
I think you're definitely ready
to go home today.
Ha ha.
They go through
so many diapers.
You see that cabinet
right there?
[JACK] Mm-hmm.
It is fully stocked.
I mean like a treasure trove.
So, um, I'm gonna step out
for a minute,
and I'm not saying
that you should take anything,
but if you did happen
to take a few things...
[laughs]
Oh, babe.
It's like the holy grail
in here.
Mm-hmm.
There's wipes.
Diapers. Oh, um...
Hey.
We can do this.
I'm gonna come back
for the rest.
Uh, I'm gonna go down
to the car.
I still have to install
the car seats, anyway.
Well, do you have the manual?
Manual?
Babe, this is...
well, this is Jack Pearson.
All right, Jack Pearson
don't need no stinkin' manuals.
[chuckles]
[grunts]
[MAN]
Hey, you need some help
with that?
No, I'm... I'm good.
I think you got those
in backward.
You might need to flip 'em.
Uh, I was... I was just checking
what the manufacturer...
Yeah, how come you got
three car seats back there?
Three babies.
Oh, God.
God bless ya.
♪ ♪
No, that's not it.
Maybe my fingers are too
muscular for this, or something.
[MAN [on video]]
Then place your base
on the seat
and adjust the foot
until there's no red visible
at the level indicator wheel.
Got it?
Okay, you're doing great.
It's like
putting a man on the moon.
[camera shutter clicking]
What the hell, man?
Oh, sorry.
I'm just a huge fan
of The Manny,and, uh...
[shutter clicks]
Well, no, you're not sorry,
because you're taking
another photo.
I'm just, I'm trying to put
my car seats
in my car, man, okay?
And I just had twins
six weeks early.
How about you just leave me with
a little bit of dignity, huh?
Sorry, uh...
Sorry about your kids.
No, um...
I'm sorry.
I... the babies are fine.
I've-I've had, like, six hours
sleep in the past four days,
and I can't sleep and I can't
stop watching them sleep,
and how do you keep them
breathing? And then the...
...car s... [sighs]
Do you have kids?
Yeah.
So you understand.
Let's get a better photo.
For reals?
For real, yeah.
[chuckles] Appreciate it.
Yeah, of course.
[camera clicks]
There you go.
Thank you so much.
I appreciate it.
Thanks for watching.
[muttering softly]
All right,
one pumpkin cream cold brew.
And for my favorite new mom
who can't have caffeine yet,
one Vanilla Steamer.
So have fun with that.
Thank you.
You're very welcome. Oof.
Big news.
Yeah?
Nurse Carmen just told me.
Guess who has two thumbs
and two newborns
and is going home today?
Real-- wow.
[sighs]
I can't wait
to sleep in my own bed.
Aren't you excited?
You said this cot
was built for R2-D2.
Yeah, no, it's... I am.
I'm-I'm thrilled.
I just, uh... we've just,
we've have a lot of help,
you know, with the doctors
and all the nurses.
It's just...
It's gonna be the two of us.
The four of us.
Right.
I can't believe we ever thought
this was hard.
I think maybe Tess was hard.
But Annie...
This girl is an angel sent
down from God himself.
Excuse me?
Nobody sent anybody down
from anywhere.
I spent two days slowly
ejecting her from my body.
You were there.
I was there.
I can't believe they're
kicking us out of here today.
I know.
Man, this place is like a spa.
Hey, girl.
Hey, guys.
And remember...
Hmm?
we are stopping by Dairy Queen
on our way home
and getting me
a Snickers Blizzard.
Yes, ma'am.
When I was in labor,
Randall promised me I could
have anything I wanted
and I chose DQ.
I could've dreamed higher,
but no regrets.
I'm gonna miss you guys.
And that one...
Don't tell the other babies,
but she's the cutest.
I know.
I think she has your eyes, Dad.
Really?
I didn't notice.
[BETH] Oh, she definitely does.
She looks like
she could start laughing
or crying at any moment.
That is all you, baby.
Ha, ha, ha.
All right, then.
She has my eyes.
You got Daddy's peepers
in there, do you?
Uh-huh. Yeah, I got you.
Huh? Yeah.
Yeah, I gotta go.
We're at the hospital.
We're gonna bring the baby
home today.
Oh, yeah, and Kate's...
Kate's here.
She's, like, right here,
so I gotta go. Bye.
Hi.
[TOBY]
You think she can read this?
[KATE]
Oh, babe.
It's so sweet.
Just so she can pick me
out of the crowd.
You ready to meet your dad?
Huh?
[laughs] Hi.
Oh, my word.
You got her?
Yeah.
Oh, she's a keeper.
Hi, there.
I'm your dad.
You can call me Dad,
or-or Dada,
or your brother
sometimes calls me Doody,
[laughs]
but I don't think
he knows what that means.
[Hailey fussing]
[TOBY [chuckles]] Yeah.
Where's Ellie?
Oh, she's just signing
the birth certificate
and the relinquishment papers,
and then she'll be right out.
All right.
Babe, I do think that we need
to be extra sensitive
with her today.
Yeah. No, I know they said
leaving the hospital
is the hardest day.
Yeah.
But, hopefully, you know,
for Ellie,
it'll be a little easier
because we're gonna send photos
and plan visits and everything.
Right.
And we will absolutely do
all those things.
Right. Right.
[TOBY]
And birth mother on your six.
[TOBY] Hi.
[KATE] Ellie.
[ELLIE]
Hi.
Oh, you guys met.
Yes. She's perfect.
I'll grab your bag.
Oh, thank you.
So how'd it go in there?
Everything's signed.
I, uh, I left a little surprise
for you guys
on the birth certificate.
First name Hailey,
middle name "zuh Comet."
[Toby and Kate laughing]
[TOBY]
I like that. I like that.
[chuckles] Thought you might.
That's good.
All right, you ready to go,
little girl?
Come on,
let me get everybody home.
[KATE]
You ready?
[softly]
Yeah.
[KATE] You got it?
[TOBY] Yeah, I think so.
[latch clicks]
♪ ♪
[clicks]
You good?
Yeah. [sighs]
Okay.
[Beth sighs loudly]
[door closes]
[RANDALL] Ready?
Hi. Ready to go.
Good?
Good job.
♪ ♪
Buckle up for safety.
[KEVIN]
Let's go home.
Hey, have I mentioned how much
of a freaking warrior you are?
Hmm.
You want music?
How about...
how about we find
that perfect first song, huh?
Yeah.
[pop song playing quietly]
[sighs]
Oh, I wish I could see them.
If there weren't three of them,
I'd be sitting in the back seat.
[groans softly]
You okay?
Yeah.
No, my-my stitches still hurt
when I turn.
Okay.
[groans]
Jack, do you think
Kate's car seat is right?
Yeah.
Are you sure?
I mean,
maybe we should just pull over.
No, baby, it's fine.
Hey, hey, babe, babe,
you're gonna hurt your...
you're gonna hurt yourself.
I'm okay, I'm okay.
[exhales]
Now, does Kevin's head
look weird to you?
No. Kevin's fine.
It seems like it's
just flopped over to one side.
What do you think
is gonna happen,
you think his head's just gonna
fall off?
[imitates soft thud]
[pop song continues quietly]
He's fine.
[baby crying loudly]
[two babies crying loudly]
Great.
It's okay, guys.
Please stop crying.
[loud crying continues]
[REBECCA]
It's okay.
[babies' crying distorting,
fading]
Pacifier?
Check.
[Annie fussing]
Sun hat?
Check.
Water for extremely thirsty
breastfeeding mom.
Mind reader!
Man, we're,
like, the dream team.
Ooh, I like that.
But if we're
gonna do basketball,
can we be the '96 Bulls?
I always saw you as Pippen
to my Jordan.
Excuse me?
I had the baby. I am Jordan.
Fair enough.
You comfortable back there?
Hundred percent not at all.
[chuckles]
I should've just sat up front.
We should think about a new car.
Pushing for that
Mercedes S-Class again?
Nah. Family car,
so we have more space.
You know,
in case we have a third.
A third what?
I said "in case."
My insides are basically
on my outsides right now,
and you're talking to me
about a third kid?
Okay, I'm sorry,
I take it back.
You know what's two things
you don't do
to a brand-new mother?
Oh... I'm sorry.
Mention having a new baby...
Mm-hmm.
...and two is
drive past the Dairy Queen
when you promised her
a Snickers Blizzard.
Copy that. All good.
I'll bust a "U" up here.
See, Annie, this is why
sometimes Jordan
just did it all
by his damn self.
[MADISON]
I am obsessed with their faces.
[KEVIN]
Yeah?
Kind of want to eat them.
[chuckles]
Not in a bad way.
[Kevin yawns]
You all good?
Yeah. No, I'm good.
I'm just tired, you know?
You need me to drive?
No. No, no, no, of course not.
You just had two babies.
You've been up all hours
of the night. I got this.
[sighs heavily]
I feel like I'm seeing things.
Okay, I am definitely driving.
No, I mean, I think we're being
followed, is what I'm saying.
This guy's been following us
the past two turns.
I think he's paparazzi.
Ooh, so, there's, like,
no traffic at all.
You must be excited
to get home, see Willow.
Yeah.
[Hailey fussing]
Oh, and I know that you said
that, you know,
you want her to meet Hailey
in a couple of weeks,
so we can definitely come down
to you, but there is this park
near our house
that has this zip line
that I think Willow
would really like.
Of course,
we're coming down there
for her birthday next month.
Oh, does she...
does Willow still like unicorns?
Or are unicorns,
like, so last week...
Yeah, she's into unicorns.
[Hailey fussing]
I will never not like unicorns.
[Kate chuckles]
It's just a couple of blocks
down on the right.
Okay.
Okay, so, uh,
we'll call you, you know,
once we're all settled in
and everything. And listen,
if you want to go
to that park that I mentioned...
Hey, I'm sorry,
but I can't, I can't do this.
What do you mean?
Um, I know that we said yes
to open adoption, and we said...
yes to visits and photos
and phone calls,
but I-I can't do it.
I can't have her in my life.
I don't know, maybe...
maybe someday
I'll be able to,
but I can't right now.
Well, maybe it's something
that we can talk about.
I mean,
how can we make it work...
Kate. Kate, Kate...
Kate, I don't want to talk
about it.
I really just want
to say goodbye to Hailey,
and I want to go home.
I'm sorry.
[softly]
It's okay.
[babies crying loudly]
It's okay, guys.
Be just a little bit longer now.
[crying continues]
[sighs] I should be
in the back with them.
I think this
is just normal crying.
[horn honking]
Yeah, going as fast
as I can, pal.
[honking horn]
I'm-I'm gonna get some gas,
fill up.
Okay.
[revving engine]
[horn honking]
[JACK] Hey!
[tires squeal]
[JACK]
Ooh!
What a maniac!
What the hell?
What the hell is it
with this guy?
[babies continue crying]
Hey, hey, hey, Jack,
let it go, let it g...
Jack!
Jack! Jack?
Hey, what are you doing, man?
I got three newborns
in that car!
[REBECCA] Hey. Jack?
That's not my problem.
Jack, get back here right now!
[MAN] Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Just...
be more careful, would you?
What is the matter with you?
We have three newborn babies
in the car.
You know what? You're right.
I'm sorry.
I'm-I'm gonna fill up.
[crying continues]
[KEVIN]
See, this is what happens
to these paparazzi.
You know, this is what happens.
They-they get tipped off by the
hospital, a nurse or an admin.
Someone tells them
when we're leaving.
That's how it happens.
[mutters]
Get rid of this guy.
Kevin, okay, Kevin, stop it.
Kevin, pull over.
No, pull over.
[stammers]
Oh, here we go. Look, our friend
here pulled over, too.
Oh, that's nice.
You want to go? Huh?
[MADISON] No. No.
You want to go? Let's go.
Kevin, Kevin, do not go. Kevin!
You want to go?
Let's go.
What the hell, man?
Just out for a drive.
You're out for a drive?
You're ruining a very special
moment between me and my family.
I'm not breaking any laws.
I'm just doing my job.
Doing your job.
Get that camera out of my face.
Get the camera out of my face.
I'm a brand-new dad-- I got
a very low threshold right now.
Keep it out of my face.
Kevin!
Kevin? Kevin, no.
Get back in the car.
I got this.
Go back to...
Don't take pictures
Kevin!
...of her, man.
Don't take a picture...
Kevin. Go back to the babies.
I've got this.
Now. Go.
Hi. I'm sorry.
We're all a little overtired
here. New parents.
Do you have kids?
No.
Nieces or nephews?
Okay, well, what if, uh,
a friend or a member
of your family...?
I don't talk to my family.
I have no friends.
I'm a very lonely person.
Okay, give me your number.
He goes jogging every Tuesday
around 9:00 a.m.
I will call you,
you can get the shot.
Shirtless?
Excuse me?
The picture's worth more
if he's not wearing a shirt.
Fine. I will make sure
he's not wearing a shirt.
Tight shorts
so I can see his package.
Ugh. That's disgusting.
Thank you.
What did you say to that guy?
Okay, Kevin, you're exhausted.
Okay? I'm gonna need you
at your best.
And aggro Liam Neeson movie
Kevin is not you at your best.
We have 20 minutes
until we get home.
I'm driving. Get some rest.
I've got this.
Here we go.
Gonna stretch my legs.
Okay. [sniffles]
I'll go in and get it for you.
One Snickers Blizzard
coming right up.
What size?
Is that even a question?
The biggest Snickers Blizzard.
A Snickers avalanche
if they have it.
No school for days
after I eat this Blizzard.
[chuckles]
I'm talking power outages
and white-out conditions.
What?
Can I just say one more thing
about not closing the door
to having a third kid?
Are you out of your mind? Do I
have to throw something at you?
I guess I always thought
that if we had two girls,
that we would go for a boy.
You did not just say
"go for a boy."
I always imagined myself
throwing the ball around
with the boy, you know, having
that special relationship?
Special relationship? You used
to go over to your mom's house
every Sunday
to watch Felicitytogether.
I...
You think that wasn't
a special relationship?
It doesn't have to be a boy.
I would love a third girl.
I'm just saying,
we make great kids.
And I don't want
to close the door.
Then, Randall,
you carry the next one.
I'm gonna get my own Blizzard.
[sighs]
[clears throat]
You're late.
You want to be on time,
get your own car.
[both laugh]
Just wrong.
Oh.
Mm.
What's this?
I know it's early, and I know
you're not telling anyone,
but I had
to get you something.
It's this old-school toy
from France.
They're like magic
for babies.
It's not gonna stay
a secret long
if you keep touching
your belly like that.
What? I didn't touch my belly.
Mm-hmm.
It is cute, right?
You're gonna love it.
It is like magic.
[both laugh]
You ready?
I'm ready. [laughs]
[indistinct chatter]
[babies crying]
[bell dings]
[crying continues]
Hey.
Uh, number four.
And these.
$12.32. Anything else?
Uh...
Yeah. Why don't...
I get one of those,
uh, little whiskeys?
And these mints?
[sniffles]
New dad. Celebrating.
All right. Congrats.
Thought you might be hungry.
Um... hey, baby, how bout...
how about you drive?
You okay to drive?
That way, I can turn around
and make sure the kids are okay.
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
She took the bottle,
and she's out.
You can just call me
"Dr. Sleep."
Wait.
No, don't do that.
It sounds... [sighs]
...murdery.
Well, great. Thank you.
I just spoke
to the babysitter,
and she's gonna bring Jack home
in half an hour, so...
Kate, there's something
I need to talk to you...
Toby, how are you not more upset
about this?
Honestly.
We signed up
for an open adoption,
and that just all changed
in a really sad blink of an eye.
Kate, I am sorry
that Ellie is hurting.
I feel bad.
But when we got into
all of this,
we knew that it was all
just a plan.
We also knew that plans change.
Toby, I grew up with a brother
who, like, didn't know
his birth parents.
That was... is... is still
really, really difficult
for him.
I know.
Okay, well, I promised myself
that it would not be like that
for Hailey.
And it won't.
Kate, adoption is a journey.
You know, and-and we don't know
when or if
Ellie is gonna change her mind,
but we will always make sure
that Hailey knows
who her birth mother is.
[Hailey crying]
I'll get her.
All right. [sighs]
[Toby sniffles]
[Hailey cries loudly]
I apologize
that you had to listen
to that little dispute
between me and your mother.
And I apologize for my
antiquated gender assumptions.
I will throw a ball with you
any day of the week.
Or watch Felicity,
whatever you like.
So you and I have the same eyes.
When the nurse said that,
it made me very happy.
Because I grew up not looking
like either of my parents,
not knowing exactly
where I came from.
So to know
that you have my eyes,
that you came from me--
that's special.
Thank you.
When I was a kid,
I had to do
a family tree for school.
And, um, I remember
making my branches,
along with my brother
and sister.
But I knew
it wasn't quite right.
They were my family,
but they weren't
where I came from.
You see, that's where you
and your sister Tess
and your mom come in.
You've provided me
with something very special.
Because you are my branches.
You are the start
of my family tree.
And I just wanted that tree
to be as big as possible.
But, hey, I guess I'm gonna have
to count on you and your sister
to have a whole lot
of grandchildren.
And then maybe one day,
I will look into the eyes
of my grandchild
or my great-grandchild,
and I will say,
"Hey, I know
where those eyes come from."
"Those eyes come
from Annie Pearson."
[sniffles loudly]
That's a peace offering?
No, they're both for me.
[Randall smacks lips, hisses]
All right.
Do not interrupt me
for the next ten minutes.
All right. I don't know
if you're ready.
I'm ready. Oh, I'm ready.
Yeah?
[engine running]
[engine shuts off]
Oh. Uh...
Are they actually...?
Let me... let me check.
All three knocked out.
[whispering]
They must have
exhausted themselves crying.
Do we bring 'em inside?
Oh, no, no, no. They say
never wake a sleeping baby.
Well, what do they say
about three sleeping babies?
I think we just wait.
Okay.
[Rebecca sighs]
[Hailey cooing]
[Kate sighs softly]
She's only happy
when I'm holding her.
So...
Like daughter, like father.
Kate, do you know why
Ellie chose us?
'Cause I like the Steelers?
Maybe. [laughs]
I'm sure
my quirky-meets-classy style
didn't hurt anything.
[chuckles]
But more than that,
she chose us, she chose you,
because she saw a funny,
beautiful,
huge-hearted mother
who has taken every challenge
that parenting has to offer
in total stride.
Kate, you're unflappable.
Really. You cannot be flapped.
All right, and-and all of this
may not be going
the way that we planned,
and Ellie may or may not be
in the picture,
but we will figure this out.
And I think Ellie knew that
from the start.
And it's a good thing
that you are...
so unflappable,
because earlier today,
when I was on the phone
with work...
I got laid off.
What?
Oh, um...
Toby, I am...
[Hailey fusses]
[sighs]
I am so sorry.
Yeah, I...
I kind of knew
that it was coming,
but I didn't want
to freak you out.
But they let, like,
40% of the staff go.
Wow.
Yeah, and I've been
torturing myself
for the last few hours
'cause I knew I had to tell you,
but I didn't want to ruin today.
You are never gonna ruin
anything,
and you're not gonna ruin
this day.
And we can figure out
the job stuff tomorrow.
Okay? Let's just be
a family today.
Me, you, and two under two.
Exactly.
Piece of cake.
See?
Unflappable.
[Franny and Nick crying
in distance]
[crying stops]
How'd you get 'em
to stop crying?
Dumb luck.
And you-- you and Mom had three.
No help, just the two of you.
How'd you manage?
Oh, that was easy.
You kids and your mom--
that was all I ever wanted.
It was easy to do it when you,
when you look at it like that.
Yeah.
They're beautiful, Kevin.
Do 'em a favor.
Stop trying to live up to me.
I was terrified of being
like my dad,
and you are terrified
of not being like yours.
We both wasted a lot of time
being quietly terrified.
Close your eyes,
decide what you want,
and then you go and get it, son.
They really are beautiful, Kev.
Hey, how long was I out?
Shh.
Uh, not long.
15 minutes.
15-- you should've woken me up.
I had it under control.
[fussing]
I think Franny's hungry.
Is that what you want?
Or maybe you just want
to be rocked-- is that it?
You just want to be rocked?
I don't know what you want.
You sound a little
like a velociraptor.
[Madison chuckles]
You okay?
Yeah, I'm great.
-Madison.
-Yeah.
Let's make this official.
I know we've been engaged,
but not engagedengaged,
and dancing around the weirdness
of it all, but I...
...I really want you
to be my wife.
I want to be a family.
Look, I will, I will get you
whatever ring that you want
whenever you want it
because you deserve that,
but until then...
[Madison laughs]
[groans]
I mean, these things are--
these are just...
[laughs]
[snaps]
There we go.
Madison.
Will you marry me?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Yeah. [laughs]
♪ ♪
It's gorgeous.
[both laugh]
[birds singing]
You know, I think this is
the quietest it's gonna be
for about 18 years.
[chuckles]
I feel like
there's the person I was
before I went to the hospital
and the person... I am now.
I barely even remember
who that girl was
who got in the car
four days ago.
I do.
I'm still me, we're still us.
Maybe.
I don't know.
I do-- hey.
I know.
My mom lost a baby
when I was five.
She had a miscarriage.
It was really early on, and...
I barely even...
registered it at the time,
but I think she was really sad.
I think she was really sad
for a long time.
What if I can't be a great mom
'cause I'm just too sad
for too long?
Hey, Rebecca, look,
I worry about a lot of things,
but I never, ever worry
about you not being a great mom.
Okay? That story's
already written.
When we stopped
at the gas station...
...I bought a little bottle
of whiskey.
I downed it right there.
I was... feeling
really overwhelmed
by everything that's happened
and I was just trying
to keep it together...
...really, 'cause when that guy
cut us off, I just-- I saw red.
Lost control.
Just like my dad would've.
Jack.
Yeah.
Every night when I was a kid,
my dad would come home
at 5:15 exactly.
And my brother and me--
we'd be playing, uh, blocks,
baseball... whatever,
just happy as clams, and...
...about 5:00, my heart
would just start pounding.
Mm.
And then I'd hear
my dad slam his car door,
and all the air would get sucked
out of the room.
He was so unhappy
just to be around us.
He-He'd have a Scotch in his
hand before he'd even say hello.
He needed it just to be
in the same house with us.
Hmm.
You are not gonna be
that kind of dad.
I don't know.
I worry.
You don't suck the air
out of the room.
You are the air.
[MAN [on radio]]
Cloudy and continuing...
["Everything I Own" by Bread
playing]
♪ You gave my life...♪
There it is.
Mm-hmm.
The perfect song.
♪ Set me free♪
♪ Set me free...♪
We're never, ever gonna be
alone in this car again
for the rest of our lives, huh?
No.
Mm.
Don't hurt yourself.
I'm okay.
♪ And I would give
anything I own♪
♪ Would give up my life,
my heart...♪
We have a family.
Yes, we do.
[whispering]
We have a family.
Gonna be one hell of a ride.
One hell of a ride.
♪ Just to have you back again♪
Hey, Jack, come on.
Come on!
Don't want to be late.
♪ You taught me how to love♪
♪ What it's of♪
♪ What
it's of♪
♪ You never said too much,
but still you showed the way♪
♪ And I knew from watching you♪
♪ Nobody else could ever know♪
[indistinct chatter]
[laughs]
♪ The part of me♪
♪ That can't let go♪
♪ And I would give
anything I own♪
♪ Would give up my life...♪
[engine shuts off]
[car doors open]
[sighs]
So, you think Uncle Kevin
ordered enough food
for a small army again?
Took you long enough.
Annie made us late.
Really?
You guys ready?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Hey, Pop.
Hi, Dad.
The beautiful, bountiful
branches of my family tree.
[DEJA]
How you holding up?
I'm okay.
I'm better for seeing you three.
You okay, Dej?
I'm fine.
Long day.
[chuckles nervously]
Um, let's, let's go see her.
[vehicle approaches, horn honks]
Hey.
Look who's here.
[horn honking]
How was the drive up?
[sighs]
Not bad.
Always goes by faster
than you'd think.