Previously, on
"This Is Us"...
Allegheny College has
a weekend QB camp
for seventh and eighth graders
right up in Meadville.
Kev would be a great fit.
I don't care what Coach says.
- I'm gonna quit.
- You're the quarterback.
You made a commitment
to that team.
You don't just quit
the second something
starts to feel tough.
He's a child playing a game.
It's supposed to be fun.
You can be really easy
on him,
and it's made him soft.
And why'd they call me?
To be honest, I have no idea.
- "To be honest"?
- Can I get that last line?
You know, I just,
if you want to
- give me a specific detail...
- NMo, no no. Stay in the scene.
I'm trying to stay in the scene,
but you keep...
- interrupting me.
- Believe me, Kevin,
- I wish I didn't have to interrupt.
- They're moving
the filming of the movie
to Vancouver.
Okay, four weeks away
puts you back here...
a solid five weeks
before the babies are due.
You have worked so hard
on this movie.
This can't all be for nothing.
I think you should use
this time away
to figure out
how these babies and I
are actually gonna fit
in your life.
*THIS IS US*
Season 05  Episode 07
Episode Title: "There"
Aired on: February 09, 2021
Synchronized by srjanapala
Jack?
Come on, let's go.
You don't want to be late
for your championship game.
Whole team's counting on
that arm of yours.
Please, please, please.
Go right, split,
8-9-7 F-motion right,
option zone.
26 off tackle...
Hey, kiddo.
You all set for this weekend?
Yeah. Just finished packing.
Okay. I'm gonna change,
and then we'll hit the road.
We should get to the hotel
about 7:00.
Make sure you get...
plenty of rest
before quarterback camp.
Cool. I'm ready whenever.
All right.
Hey, you know, they're...
they're saying
that there's gonna be two QBs
from Penn State there.
You do good this weekend,
word is gonna spread quick that
you're the next Terry Bradshaw.
Mm-hmm.
Can't wait.
Yeah.
Objection!
All due respect, Your Honor,
this is a man here who knowingly
misrepresented the evidence.
That's good.
All due respect, Your Honor,
we're dealing with a man...
Your Honor... No.
- Judge...
Judge, Your Honor,
all due respect,
this is a man who knowingly
misrepresented the evidence.
I object. And furthermore...
...furthermore...
Yeah.
Uh...
Oh, hey.
Hey. Thank you
for the edible arrangement.
It is... elaborate, Kev.
- And kind of romantic.
- Was it?
Oh, see?
I told them to take it easy
on the chocolate-covered
strawberries.
I just, I wasn't sure what the
appropriate gift would for...
when the birth mother
of your twin sister's baby
is being induced.
Uh, it's actually a Tesla.
Well, okay, they were all out
of chocolate-covered Teslas.
All right? So... so how are,
uh, how are you two doing?
What's going on?
Are you guys excited?
Yeah.
Yeah. We're just waiting
for Jack's sitter to get here,
and then, um, we're
gonna head down to San Pedro
and meet Ellie
at the hospital, so...
How's Vancouver?
How's the movie?
Movie is going great.
Actually, tonight is
my big courtroom scene...
You know, the one
where I cross-examine De Niro?
That sounds terrifying.
Yeah, yeah, it's my big "did
you order the Code Red" moment.
Every time I think about it,
I pee a little.
Ew, that's gross.
Okay, so you are back
next week?
Mm-hmm, yep.
Thank God, back next week,
and I swear I'm not leaving
the house for, like, a month.
All I'm gonna do is stare
at Madison's belly
and just wait for the twins
to make their big debut.
Oh...
Oh, hey, um, Jack's, uh,
sitter is here, so I gotta go.
Okay. Well, uh, listen,
keep me posted and, uh
tell the birth mother
I said "happy pushing."
Uh, not gonna do that.
But, hey, will you tell De Niro
that I loved him
in Meet the Fockers.
Not gonna do that.
Okay, fine. I love you.
I love you, too. Bye.
Whew.
- What's up, man?
- Hey.
De Niro's still
in hair and makeup,
but I figured you'd want to be
on set when he got there.
Yeah, good call. Not a man
you want to keep waiting, right?
No.
Hey, honey.
Listen, uh, I'm about ready
to start shooting with De Niro.
Is there a way I can call you...
Kevin, I think
I'm having contractions.
What? No, no, no, we're supposed
to have another couple weeks.
It might just be Braxton-Hicks,
but, um,
I've had those before,
and they don't feel like this.
Um, I called Dr. Alexander,
and she said I should
come in right away.
It's good
that she's being cautious.
Maybe-maybe it's a false alarm.
Maybe, but, um,
I don't think so.
Okay, um, I gotta go.
I'll...
I'll call you when
I get to the hospital.
Just... pick up if you can.
Yeah, I...
Hey.
Hey, Kevin, uh,
De Niro should be here
in, like, five,
and then we'll do
a rehearsal, all right?
Sounds... sounds good.
Listen, I think my fiancée's
in-in labor.
Oh, wow.
That's awesome.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Six weeks early.
And I know with twins
it's normal to be early,
but that's, like, three weeks.
This is... six weeks.
Well, look, I'm-I'm sure
it'll be fine.
You know, my brother, uh,
he had his son super early,
and the kid just graduated
valedictorian,
so...
Cool.
She, you know, she's, uh...
She seemed pretty scared.
And she's alone.
I think I should go to her.
Okay. Okay, look, uh,
I'll try and move
quickly here.
We could probably get this
in six or seven hours,
and then, uh,
I'll talk to Steve.
Uh, and we can push
all the pick-up days
so we can get you out of here
first thing tomorrow. Okay?
- How does that sound?
- I don't think that's gonna work.
What are you saying, Kevin?
- De Niro is walking. Here in two.
- Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Foster.
Tell him I said I am very sorry,
but I gotta go.
W...
How you feeling?
Ready to pitch a no-hitter?
Yeah, Dad. Feeling good.
Come on, get in.
Gonna be some adventure.
Ready?
- Hey.
- Hey, how we doing?
On my way to the hospital.
I really don't think
these are fake contractions.
Okay, listen. Uh, I'm coming.
Okay? I'm coming,
I'm leaving right now.
- You are?
- Yeah. Just hang in there, all right?
I promise, I will...
I will get to you, all right?
Always exciting seeing
a game end
in a walk-off home run.
Just not when your kid's
the pitcher.
I only gave up one run.
It's not my fault
the guys weren't hitting.
Yeah, that sounds like
an excuse to me.
Hey, Dad, maybe we should,
uh...
wait around a bit
- before going home.
- Why?
I just, um...
What... you-you think
I can't drive?
No. I just...
Fine.
You drive, hotshot.
First time for everything.
♪ Far away ♪
♪ All you got to do
right now is say... ♪
Did I ever tell you
I played Little League
when I was a kid?
Yeah.
I was a pretty good pitcher.
Had all these dreams about
being the next Bob Friend.
Who?
You don't know who Bob Fr...?
I guess it was
a little ahead of your time.
So, Bob Friend
was a four-time all-star.
Helped the Pirates
win the 1960 World Series.
1960?
How old are you?
Ha, ha, ha.
- Whoa.
- Hmm?
Football camp
is really expensive.
Nah. Kev, don't...
don't worry about that.
Now, when you get a football
scholarship to Penn State,
this weekend is gonna be
the best investment I ever made.
I don't care
where my seat is. I do not care
what airline it is.
I just need to get
on the next flight to L.A.
I'm on my way to Vancouver
Airport right now, and I will
literally get on whatever flight
you can book for me.
Hmm. I'm not seeing
anything direct from Vancouver
to Los Angeles
until tomorrow morning.
I can't do tomorrow morning.
I... What about indirect?
Well, how do you
feel about flying economy?
I know you're big on
legroom.-
Well, at this point,
I'll cut my legs off.
Just get me
on the next flight to L.A.
- Anything, honey?
- Yes.
- Oh, your mom has one.
- What? Yes!
Great! Thank God.
What time?
Oh, wait. No, sorry. I...
I-I put in the code
for Victorville, not Vancouver.
There are a lot of flights
from Victorville, though.
Yeah, but I said...
I'm not in Victorville, Mom.
Why didn't the movie
give you an assistant
to do these kind of things?
You know,
it's-it's an indie film.
It's a smaller budget,
and I-I told them
I'd take one for the team and...
and go without,
which I am deeply regretting
at the moment. -
Geez!
S-Sorry,
some maniac just cut me off.
Kev, be careful.
Me? I'm... I am be...
I'm being careful.
Wait, wait, wait. Hold
on, hold on. Good news, good news.
Uh, it looks like there are
a few domestic flights
left tonight.
- Oh.
- Kevin,
just keep driving
towards the border.
We're gonna try to book you
something out of Seattle,
- and we'll call you back.
Okay? -
Okay, great.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
I j... I...
Sorry, I got to take this.
My agent won't stop
hounding me.
- Hello?
- Please tell me
you didn't really walk out
on De Niro.
Madison's in labor,
and she's six weeks early.
Oh, God.
Okay, how close is she
to giving birth?
'Cause maybe we
get you back to L.A.,
you meet the babies,
and we have you back
in Vancouver
- by tomorrow morning.
- You got...
I-I'm not doing this, man. Look, I...
I got to go.
Hey. How's it going?
Okay.
I'm here.
I'm, uh, I'm waiting for a room.
I'm not in active labor,
so nobody seems to be
in a rush to see me.
But what about
your private room?
You're supposed to have
a private room.
They're trying to find one.
I'm six weeks
before my due date.
- Nobody was expecting me.
- No, no, no.
No, no, no. Th-They said
that the room would be ready
when-when you're in labor.
And you're in labor,
so the room should be ready,
right? I'll handle this.
- Kevin, it's okay.
- No. No, it's not okay.
You should have a private room.
I got a card
right here from the hospital
with a direct line
I'm supposed to call
if something like this happens.
I'm gonna call right now,
and I'm gonna go
full Terms of Endearment
on their ass.
Where are you?
I'm, uh...
I'm on my way to the airport.
Miguel and my mom
are trying to book me a flight.
So, hopefully, I'll be there
in the next couple hours.
Okay.
I'm coming. I promise.
Madison, I'll be there.
Okay.
- Randall, hey.
- Hey, Kev.
We're driving home
from New Orleans.
A long story.
I was wondering
if we could talk.
Randall, I'm sorry.
I can't right now, okay?
My whole life
has... been turned upside down.
Madison's in labor,
and I'm stuck
here in Vancouver.
I'm trying to get home
in time for the births,
but she's already
at the hospital, and...
She's all alone.
I never...
Never should have come here.
Hey, Kev...
Randall, I'm sorry.
I'll-I'll call you soon, okay?
I'm sorry.
Hello?
Hey. Kevin, this is Foster.
I know, um...
I know you're really emotional
right now, but I...
I do need you to turn around
and come back to set
immediately.
Now, shut up. Just shut...
You know what? Shut up.
Just shut your mouth.
Stop talking. No one cares
about your stupid movie!
I quit.
Any day now.
Come on, come on, come on.
They can really help.
Some of 'em got a good arm.
- Look who it is.
- Jack.
- Coach.
- Kevin.
- I'm so glad you made it.
- Us, too.
Hey, this is Jason and Richard.
They both play for Penn State.
They sure do.
They're gonna be, uh,
running drills
with us tomorrow.
Yeah, I'm excited to see
what you can do
- on the field, little man.
- Yeah.
It's time to see if anything
I've said in practice
has actually gotten through
to you.
Oh, it has.
Yeah, we're ready.
Hey.
You okay?
- Did you get a flight yet?
- No.
Not yet. I'm still waiting
for Miguel to call me back.
How's everything going
over there?
The doctor just left.
She said everything
looked totally good and normal.
They're already at a
healthy weight to be born.
Fully cooked.
Not even medium rare?
No, perfectly medium.
Just like I like 'em.
- This is getting away from us.
- Yes, it is.
But it's not Braxton-Hicks.
I'm in labor.
The contractions
have slowed down a little bit,
which they said is normal, but, um...
But I am definitely in labor.
They're coming.
Well, you keep
those contractions slow, okay?
Because I'm coming, too.
I'll do my best.
I think it's
time to shift those babies,
like we talked about.
Is there anything I can do
to help? Um, anyone
you want me to talk to?
I mean, I-I know
your entire birth plan,
so if you want
to put a-a nurse or a doctor
on the phone,
- I can walk them through the whole thing.
- Hey, Kevin,
I got to go.
Um, they're gonna put
a bunch of pillows
underneath m to try to change
the babies' position a little.
Labor is crazy.
Um, I'll call you later.
Yeah, okay. Um, you know,
I'm here if you need anything.
I can...
Hey. I was just about
to call you.
We got you a flight.
Yes! G-Great. What airport?
Seattle. It boards in two hours
Can you make it?
Yes, I can. Yes, I can make it.
How long's the flight?
- It's two and a half hours.
- Two and a half hours.
Okay, that puts me there
in about...
five hours.
First births usually take
a little longer, right?
Which means
I am probably gonna make it.
Miguel. Miguel, I swear to God,
if you were here right now,
I'd kiss you right on the mouth.
- Thank you.
- I mean,
I would regret it
immediately afterwards,
but in the heat of the moment,
I would kiss you
- right on those beautiful lips.
- Yeah, okay.
I'll text you
the boarding pass, okay?
Thank you.
Oh, hey, Miguel,
- can I talk to my mom?
- Oh, yeah, of course.
- Wants to talk to you.
- Oh.
Hi, sweetheart.
You're having a little bit
of an unexpected adventure, huh?
Yeah.
Not really how I imagined it.
Yeah. It never is.
I just... I wanted
delivery day to be perfect.
You know,
I wanted to be there for her,
waiting on her hand and foot.
I wanted to be like...
Your father.
Kev,
I know you put him
on a pedestal.
And-and I don't blame you.
He was a wonderful father.
I pro...
Not on...
My... Bir...
- Yeah.
- Are you kidding? Mom?
Mom, you're breaking up
pretty bad. Are you...
I don't even know
if you can hear this, but I...
I'm gonna have to call you...
Oh. Perfect.
Oh, no.
Damn it.
All right.
You know what's always
been the trouble with you?
You spend too much time stuck
in that damn head of yours.
Come on!
Go faster. At this rate, we
ain't gonna be home till winter.
You know, I told your mother
when you signed up,
we were just throwing our money
down the drain.
But she don't care. She's always
been totally crappy with money.
Shut up!
My lips are sealed there,
hot shot.
Feel a little better?
Yeah.
Must've been Mom's Sloppy Joes.
Kev, what's going on?
What if I suck tomorrow?
You're not gonna suck tomorrow.
But what if I do?
What if I'm not actually
that good at football?
That means I have nothing.
Nothing?
Kev, what are you talking about?
You and Mom talk about it
all the time.
Randall's a genius,
and all I have is football.
That is not all you have.
I heard you and Mom talking
the other day.
You told her I was soft.
Look, I don't know exactly
what you overheard,
but that's not what I meant.
Yes, it is,
or you wouldn't be here.
What is that supposed to mean?
We never do anything
alone together.
But you took the time
to bring me here, because...
you think that football's
my only shot at being special.
That's what you think I think?
I know that's what you think.
And Coach doesn't think
I have what it takes.
He just yells at me
all the time.
He... That's just his style,
Kev, okay?
Coach is old-school.
He wouldn't have
brought you here
if he didn't think
you were good enough.
He calls me names, and...
he says I'm stupid.
He calls you "stupid"?
Kevin?
He tells me I'm stupid pretty
much every day of my life.
You know what? Let's, um...
Let's go get you some food,
okay?
Let's settle that stomach
of yours.
- Dad, I'm not hungry.
- Come on.
I have a super early morning.
I think I should just go to bed.
Get your sweater. Let's go.
Thank God.
We got to get you out of here.
- Call an ambulance!
- No, I can't get a signal.
You're gonna be all right,
though, okay?
I'll get you to a hospital.
Gonna get you out of here.
Come on.
All right. Come on.
- Come on, come on!
- My leg is stuck.
It hurts really bad.
Okay, listen. Listen to me.
Listen to me.
On the count of three, I'm gonna
pull up on the steering wheel,
- and you're gonna pry your leg out, okay?
- Oh, God. Okay.
Breathe. Just breathe.
Listen to me. One, two, three.
Go, go. Come on. Come on.
There you go.
All right. Come on. I got you.
Come on. Here we go.
Hey. Hey!
Oh, damn it. Okay.
Hey. Listen to me.
You're all right.
I'm gonna get you out
of here, okay?
Hey, come on.
Come with me. Got to get you
to a hospital. Come on.
Hey, let's go.
We got this. Let's go.
Hi. Um, want to eat
at the bar with your old man?
- Yeah.
- We're... Thanks.
Go on, pick a seat.
Hi. We're gonna get two New York
strips, uh, medium... rare?
- A side of onion rings?
- Yeah.
And two Cokes.
- Sure thing.
- Thanks.
This place is pretty cool.
Yeah.
♪ Every time... ♪
Listen to me.
Yes, when you made starting
quarterback, I was psyched,
because it was exciting
to watch you shine.
But Kevin, football is not
the only thing that you have.
Do you understand?
Yeah.
Two Cokes.
♪ Won't you stay? ♪
You know, my dad used to come
to my Little League games.
Never missed them.
It was the one thing
he always showed up for.
And he made them
a living hell for me.
He'd get drunker and drunker,
inning by inning.
If my team won,
at least he was a happy drunk,
slapping me on the arm
and calling me "Jackie Boy"
the whole ride home.
But if we lost...
I started praying
before every game.
'Cause a good game meant
a good car ride home.
Baseball, this thing
that I loved...
it became all about him.
I mean, ev-every pitch I threw,
I could... I could hear
his voice in my ear.
You know?
"Don't screw this up, Jack."
"Get out of your head, Jack."
"What a waste
of a Sunday, Jack."
I didn't know he was like that.
Mm. Yeah.
You never really
talk about him.
Yeah, well,
being out on the road
and sitting at a bar with my son
makes a guy want to open up.
Yeah, he-he wasn't all bad,
my dad.
Uh, that's what makes
our parents loom so large
in our heads, I think.
They're...
a million things to us
all at once.
Not bad.
Didn't know you had it in you.
Indy 500, watch out.
Keys.
And even
after they're long gone,
we're stuck with them.
Can't help it.
They're inside of us.
You know, my whole life,
I promised myself
I'd be nothing like him, but...
...here I am, putting all
this pressure on you,
making you so nervous,
you're sick.
I ended up just like him.
No, Dad.
You're way better than him.
Thank you, my son.
And you're gonna be
way better than me.
Maybe.
Well, I'm gonna go
to the bathroom, bud.
Uh, don't pick up any girls
while I'm gone.
Coach?
Oh, hey, Jack.
Hey, Kevin excited?
Oh, it's a big day tomorrow.
I want you to know, I'm not
gonna miss a game this season.
Well, of course not.
I mean, got to watch your boy,
right?
I'm not just gonna be
watching him.
Don't ever call my kid stupid.
Ever.
- Jack...
- Tell me you understand.
Hey, Coach.
Hey, Kevin.
See you tomorrow.
Hey.
Coach was here.
Yeah.
Did you see him?
- In the bathroom?
- Yeah, for a minute.
- Mmm.
- Did you say something to him?
Nope.
Mmm. Now, that's good.
Yeah. I like it a little bloody.
Hey, it's
Madison. Leave a message.
Hey, I'm checking in. Uh...
Boy, do I have a story for you.
Anyway, uh, Miguel got me
on a flight out of Seattle.
I think I can make it. Um...
Hey, I'm really trying here.
You know? Um...
Just call me when you get this,
if you can.
Wait a second.
Aren't you...
Kevin Pearson, yeah.
Life is so weird.
Yeah.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey, hey, hey.
Let's keep talking.
Look at... five minutes.
We got five minutes, okay?
We're at the hospital
in five minutes.
Just keep talk... um...
That was my fiancée,
on the phone there.
She's-she's pregnant. She's
in labor, actually, with twins.
And I'm probably gonna
miss my flight.
Which means I'm gonna miss
my children being born.
the most important moment
of their lives.
I have three teenagers.
They don't remember anything
before kindergarten.
This is not the most
important day of their lives.
They're not
even gonna remember it.
You're rich, you're famous.
You're gonna be
their freakin' idol.
None of that stuff matters, man.
You know, my dad wasn't
either of those things.
He was just there.
Always.
My dad was the most there person
that ever lived.
Everything that I do,
I do with his voice in my head.
He would have
rescued you tonight,
he would've saved you.
And he would have made it
to the births, he would've...
figured out a way to do it all.
He believed I could be
that kind of person, too.
Hey! Little help?
We need a wheelchair.
Hey, listen, my phone
is about ready to die
but I made it to the airport.
I think I'm gonna make it there
in time, Madison.
I can feel it, okay?
Hang tight, bye.
Hey. I'm TSA PreCheck.
- Great. Just need your ID.
- Yeah.
Oh, you got to be kidding.
No, no, no, no... oh, um...
Oh, no. Okay... uh...
There was an accident.
There-there was an accident.
You're not gonna believe this,
but there was an accident.
I had to pull a guy
out of his car
and drive him to the hospital.
Wow, that's amazing.
Thank you.
Yeah, it's just that my, um,
my-my ID, it was in my jacket,
and the jacket... I gave...
I gave that man my jacket.
Or-or it fell out or something...
Anyway, I...
I don't have my ID on me.
I'm so sorry, sir.
I can't let you on the plane
without your ID.
Right, yeah, it's just, um...
Look, uh...
I'm Kevin Pearson,
I'm-I'm a public figure.
I'm not trying to say that
to get special treatment,
I'm-I'm saying that
because it's just, you know,
it's... you can look me up,
it's very easy to figure out
who I am,
you can look me up online.
My whole damn life is online.
That's not really how it works.
There's an office where
you can request an emergency ID.
- Usually takes about a day.
- I don't have a day.
Okay? My fiancée right now is in
Los Angeles and she's in labor.
I need to get to her, please.
You got to let me
on that flight.
I'm really sorry.
I wish I could help,
but it's really not up to me.
Listen, I can't start off
by not being there for them.
You need to understand that.
I can't. I don't...
I don't know how else
to explain it to you, okay?
It will break me.
I'm begging you, please,
figure out a way
to get me on that flight.
Only three centimeters.
We have a ways to go.
But these things can speed up
quickly sometimes.
There's really no telling.
Hang in there.
Everything okay?
I just, um,
I can't believe
I'm maybe gonna do this alone.
Why don't you call someone?
Mom, friend?
It might help pass the time.
I'm not close to my mom.
Or anyone in my family, really.
To be honest, there's really
only two people in the world
I am truly close to, and, um...
well, one of them is having
a baby of her own
and the other
is hopefully on a plane.
But who knows?
I can't reach him.
I have to check
on my other mamas,
but I'll come back
as soon as I can, okay?
Hello?
Hi, Madison. It's Randall.
- And Beth.
Um, I spoke to Kevin.
I know he's trying
to get to you,
but we just wanted to say
if you need anything
in the meantime,
don't hesitate to call.
Uh, we're still driving back
from New Orleans,
so if you want us to have
some food sent over there
or anything,
we-we just want you to know
that we're here.
Okay.
Uh, thank you.
Um, or if you want,
we can stay on the phone
with you for a while.
No.
No, no, um, I'm-I'm fine.
You sure?
Madison, we really can
stay on with you.
You're family.
Okay.
Um...
Yeah, that'd be
really nice, actually.
Of course.
As long as you need.
Synchronized by srjanapala