Previously on This Is Us...
I just got six messages
from the adoption agency.
We have a match.
Kate and Toby?
-Hi.
Hi.
-Hi. I'm-I'm Ellie.
Thank you
for the Edible Arrangement.
I wasn't sure what
the appropriate gift would be
for when the birth mother
of your twin sister's baby
is being induced.
Hey, Kev. I was wondering
if we could talk.
Randall, I'm sorry,
I can't right now.
Madison's in labor,
and I'm stuck here in Vancouver.
I'll call you soon, okay?
I'm sorry.
-Got you a flight.
Yes!
-G-Great. What airport?
-Seattle.
It boards in two hours.
Can you make it?
Listen, I can't start off
by not being there for them.
I don't know how else
to explain it to you, okay?
It will break me.
I can't believe I'm maybe gonna do this alone.
-Hello?
-Hi, Madison.
We just want you to know
that we're here.
And we can stay on the phone
with you for a while.
-You're family.
-Okay.
Yeah, that'd be really nice.
♪ Whenever I'm with him♪
♪ Something inside...♪
All right, in there
I've found a Swede,
a South African, two Thais,
a Scot and a Brit.
Does a Scot count as a Brit?
Eh, doesn't matter.
What are you
and do you have a light?
I don't.
I'm sorry.
I'm Nasir. From India.
Esther. From Argentina.
And I need a light.
Aye. New Mexico
isn't quite what I imagined.
It's dustier.
Very big food.
The first day I got here,
I got a hamburger,
like, the size of my head.
You don't talk much, huh?
My advisor insisted I come.
Try and make friends, but...
I-I can't put this down.
Advanced Computer Programming.
-Anything good?
It's about Turing's development
of his a-machine
and how in proving
the uncomputability
of the Entscheidungsproblem
by such a machine,
he showed
the fundamental limitations
of mechanical computation.
I have no idea
what you are talking about.
But I know I love
hearing you talk.
Hey, kids,
grab your bags.
I want to load the car now
so we can
hit the road for the cabin
at 8:00 a.m. sharp.
And I'm gonna go, uh, make
some sandwiches for lunch,
so let me know
what you guys want, okay?
Guys, we don't want to go.
-Wait, what?
-Huh?
-Of course you do.
Hey, sorry, Dad,
but the cabin is lame.
-Very lame.
No, no, no, no, no.
The cabin is not lame.
The cabin is... relaxation.
Yeah.
-The cabin is fresh air
-and s'mores and...
-Look, we all set up sleepovers
for the weekend.
Parent-approved.
You can call them.
Cancel your plans, all right?
We're going on a family vacation
this weekend,
-and that's the end of...
-Uh, babe?
Could I talk to you?
Would it be the worst thing
in the world to go away
without the little grumps?
Think about it, come on.
You, me, romantic cabin getaway,
let the kids be someone else's
problem for the night?
You and me,
romantic cabin getaway?
Yeah.
Hey.
Sleepover drop-off train
leaves at 8:00 a.m. sharp.
Yes.
This is Kevin.
Leave a message.
-Kev's phone
still going to voice mail?
-Yeah.
So I have no idea
if he made his flight or not.
Can you imagine
if he misses this?
He won't.
At least Randall and Beth
got in touch with her
from New Orleans
-so she's not alone.
-True. True.
I should be with them.
I'm supposed to be with them.
Mm...
Looks like they forgot
the special sauce.
-Oh, man!
-I know.
We did not just find
the only place open
in the middle of nowhere,
Alabama,
-and they didn't give me
the special sauce.
-Mm-hmm.
Are you guys sure
you don't want to go?
'Cause I can hang up.
I know it's late for you,
and, um,
and, you know, I'm sure
you need to find a motel
-for the night.
Oh, uh-uh.
I have not done my own hair
and nails
and waxing
for the better part of a year
just to get COVID
from some rank motel off I-81.
Hey, Madison,
for the 20th time,
we're not hanging up.
We are with you
until Kevin gets there.
If anything,
you're doing us a favor, right?
You're giving us
a little roadside entertainment
as we take turns driving
and shotgunning Red Bulls
for the next 14 hours.
I know this isn't
exactly how you imagined
the births of these babies,
but I do believe
that Kevin is out there
trying his damnedest
to get to you
and that he will be there
in time for
your unfairly gorgeous babies
to be born.
And if, for some reason,
he doesn't,
then you got a couple
of real live
baby birthing experts right here
to see you through it every step of the way. We can handle it.
Beth had a natural birth
with Tess
right in our living room.
-Kevin?
-Um...
Ah, it's Kate.
Uh, family text thread.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Hey, babe.
-How's it going?
-Mm-hmm. Hi.
Hey, group texts?
No way, Kate.
Absolutely not.
If I can't be
in the delivery room because of
stupid COVID,
then I demand personalized,
individualized updates.
Okay. Okay.
Listen, the only update
is that I'm being
a really great birth partner
to a birth
-that is...
-So freaking slow.
How long have we been here,
like, a hundred hours?
Eight.
A breezy eight. Oh, babe,
have you had any updates
from the sitter?
Uh, yeah, Jack is fine.
I'm the one out here
in the, uh, hospital parking lot
losing my mind.
Everything is fine, I promise.
And I will update you
when there is
an update worth sharing.
Okay? Hey, so, uh,
how's your list coming?
Uh, my list?
Uh, you'll just... You'll know
when you know. How about that?
-Fine, be mysterious. Oh, hey.
-The nurse is here.
Got to go. Bye.
-Okay.
Hi, there.
-Hi.
-Hey.
-My name is Joan.
I'm taking over for Rachel.
Oh, did you hear that, Kate?
We've been here
for a whole nurse shift,
and my cervix
is still refusing to budge.
Things speed up eventually.
They always do.
Just hang in there, Mom.
Sorry, um,
I just want to make sure
that everyone
on the delivery team remembers
that Kate
is the adoptive mother.
She is Mom.
I am just a temporary landlord
with an eviction notice.
I am so sorry.
I should've checked your file
-before I came in. I meant no...
-It's okay. It's okay.
But please do remind everyone
that when the baby is here,
she should go directly to Kate.
Not to me.
Will do.
Page me if you need anything.
-Okay.
Thank you.
-Thanks.
I mean,
it's as if she's never had
a woman giving birth
to her one-night-stand baby
with the adoptive mother
as the birth partner
in the middle
of a global pandemic.
I know.
It's, like, old-fashioned.
Hey.
I'm really grateful that
you're here with me for this.
Well, I'm really grateful
that you asked me.
Really.
So, let's have this baby.
I cannot wait to start a fire
and just sit around
in my cozy socks all weekend.
Is that all
you're gonna be wearing?
-Because I can
get on board with that.
-Ha-ha.
You know what the best part is?
-What's that?
-Not having to hear
Kate recite the plot
of this week's 90210.
Oh, yeah. She's, uh,
kind of obsessed, huh?
Honestly, I can't even tell
if it's a terrible show
or if she's just terrible
at recapping it.
And you know what else
-I'm psyched
to not have to listen to?
-Okay.
Kevin and Randall bickering
about everything.
I mean,
here is to an entire weekend
-without having to hear
the word "buttmunch."
-Mm-hmm.
Oh, babe.
Do you feel
that bliss settling in?
That is the bliss
of an entire weekend
-with no surly teenage
interruptions.
-Yeah.
Oh, no.
-Jack, come here.
-What?
Oh, what the hell?
All right,
I found 30 years' worth
of dusty old board games
to keep us busy.
Did you put yourself
into a time-out?
No, there's better Wi-Fi
over here.
I-I didn't know if the kids
were trying to call or text me
and maybe
I just didn't have service.
Do you want to go upstairs
and watch TV instead?
No, I don't want to watch TV.
I want my kids to call me
with more information.
I want to teleport
my body to Los Angeles.
I want...
I want a cocktail.
No, I'm-I'm not kidding.
Are you sure? The doctor said
with the meds, you could...
One drink every once in a while
would not kill me.
And in this case,
I feel like
it might actually save my life.
Well, I mean, how would
a cocktail really compare
A Game of Truth or Dare?
Or your life.
Me having a cocktail
might save your life.
One cocktail coming right up.
Thank you.
Oh, come on.
So, yeah. Apparently,
we own a farmhouse
in New Orleans now.
Randall, that-that story
is insane.
You're not wrong.
Okay.
Those last few have been
pretty intense.
Maybe we should call the nurse.
You okay to keep driving
for a while?
Mm, yeah.
It's your time to shine, baby.
Okay.
Hey.
You're in my spot.
I can see, like, ten empty spots
just in my line of vision.
-I'm not even looking
over there.
-Great.
Just move
into one of those, then.
Um... I...
I'm sorry, sir.
Do you not see
my elaborate setup?
I'm loving it.
This-this elaborate setup
kind of makes me wish
I had gone to a football school
where I could've
tailgated every weekend
for four years.
-And I hate football.
-You know, I don't give
a rat's ass. Just move it.
Buddy, I'm just waiting
for my daughter
to be born, okay?
And I'm waiting to find out
if my wife is gonna live or die.
Oh.
55 years attached at the hip.
Now I'm down here,
and she's up there,
attached to a ventilator.
This freakin' virus.
And I've been coming here
every night,
and I always park in that spot.
Number 157.
It's her favorite number.
It's the first house
we ever lived in.
157 Overhill Road.
She's always been superstitious
about that kind of stuff.
Like a special number
had some sort of a...
a magical power.
Am I really gonna have to ask
you to move your car again?
No, sir, you are not.
I'm moving right now.
I'm moving.
He's perfect.
He looks just like me.
This baby
is a mathematical anomaly.
He's a product
greater than the constants
multiplied to make him.
I hate to break it to you,
my son,
but your father is a giant geek.
All right,
these should be drinkable.
-There you go.
Thank you.
-Salud.
-Cheers.
-Whew!
-Ah.
I didn't have much to work with.
That liquor cabinet
hasn't been updated
-in 20-plus years, so I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry.
I know you love anisette,
but this...
this tastes like car fuel.
-Car fuel? Wow.
Yeah, it does.
Now, I seem to remember
you had more than one shot
of chichaítos in Puerto Rico
after our wedding.
Excuse me.
I was in Puerto Rico.
I was married. I was happy.
Will you please give
an old lady a break.
-Just this once. Just this once.
Pipe in the upstairs
bathroom burst.
Yeah, the whole room is just...
it's flooded.
-Oh.
-I'm gonna go
to the hardware store,
get some stuff to stop all that.
What was in the boxes?
Um, well, that's some of
the kids' old art
we brought from home.
We were gonna frame it
and put it up,
but we just never
got around to it.
Oh, man.
Everything's ruined.
Come on. It's not like
our kids' crappy art
was gonna make it
in The Met or anything.
Right.
That was a good one, Bec.
-What?
-Nothing.
It's just, you've...
You've been ripping
on the kids all day.
No, I haven't.
Look, forget it.
Doesn't matter.
You're right, the box is ruined.
-Let's just toss it and move on.
-Jack.
I'm gonna go
to the hardware store,
get something to fix that.
I'll be back soon.
What's with you?
Baby's on the way.
Uh, I'd be pacing back and forth
in the waiting room if I could,
but don't worry, I'll-I'll stay
over here in my-my zone.
I won't get too close.
Uh, are those...
are those pigs on your...
Pigs are a thing with Rose,
my wife.
We went to Austria
on our honeymoon
because The Sound of Music
came out that year and...
she wanted to see Salzburg.
I get it.
I made Kate move to Pasadena
just for the
Back to the Future house.
We were there over New Year's.
Turns out the Austrians
go all out for pigs
over New Year's.
Pigs on platters
and marzipan pigs,
little pig tchotchkes
in all the markets.
They say they bring good luck.
So...
to start our marriage off right,
we bought this little sucker.
And over the years, whenever
we needed a little luck...
You found yourself a pig.
Figured I'd bring the whole
bacon army out for this one.
They say they might be able
to take her off
the ventilator soon, but...
Hey, that's...
you know, that's not...
that's not nothing, right?
So you, uh...
you haven't been able
to go inside at all, huh?
No.
She made me promise
not to visit.
She didn't want me
getting sick, too.
If you think I'm stubborn,
you ought to meet my Rose.
Yeah.
Kate can be
kind of stubborn, too.
Is that why you're out here?
She kick you out
of the delivery room?
Oh, uh, no.
We're actually adopting.
Yeah, she's in there
with the birth mom,
and there's only one
visitor allowed.
But we made a deal--
since she gets to be in there,
I get to pick the middle name.
Anything I want.
She has no veto rights.
-That's a lot of pressure.
-Yeah.
Yeah, I have
quite the list going on.
I'm having a hard time
whittling it down.
I don't want to pick it out
just yet.
You know?
I want to wait till she's here,
until she's officially ours.
Just don't want to jinx it.
Here.
One of Rose's favorites.
Once the anesthetic is in,
you'll start to feel relief
in about 15 minutes.
So, can you lean forward
and round your shoulders,
please?
Oh, no, no. No way.
Hell no. I am...
-I am all the way out. No.
Hey, Madison,
Madison, Madison.
Don't look at the needle.
Look at me.
Okay? Just focus
on these calming baby browns.
Oh, God.
Oh, God, I just looked
at it again, Randall.
Distract me.
Please tell me a story that has
-nothing to do with this.
-Yeah.
Okay, uh, when I decided
to become a city councilman,
I had to...
-Come on, give her
something interesting.
Okay.
His junior prom,
Kev comes home wasted.
Uh, reminder that I'm having
this recovering alcoholic's
babies right now.
Yeah, but this was
back when he was just
a charming rascal teen
having one too many,
so just go with me here, okay?
Uh, I intercept him before
our parents know he's home.
I take him down to his room,
tell him to take off his shoes
so he can get into bed.
Go to get him a glass of water,
I come back,
and he is completely naked,
-belting "MMMBop"
at the top of his lungs.
I mean, my man is going for it.
He's shaking
his little pasty ass,
literally jumping up and down
on his bed doing air drums.
God, Kevin.
-I keep telling him
to shut the hell up
before he wakes up our parents.
Then, suddenly,
he stops-- right?--
and he stares at me,
just dead serious.
I think he's about
to hurl everywhere,
and then he just says,
"Dude, how come we never
started a brother band?
-"Like Hanson.
"We could be Pearson.
We could be rock stars, man."
A little pinch.
Hey, Madison, look at me.
Can you imagine it?
Me and Kev on a world tour?
♪ Uh-huh♪
♪ Oh, yeah♪
♪ Mmm bop, ba duba dop♪
♪ Ba du bop, ba duba dop♪
Come on.
Join in in our band. Come on.
♪ Dooby da ba doo-wop♪
There she is!
♪ Mmm bop, ba duba dop♪
♪ Ba du bop, ba duba dop♪
-♪ Ba du bop, ba duba dop♪
♪ Ba du♪
♪ Mmm bop, ba duba dop♪
♪ Ba du bop♪
♪ Yeah, yeah.♪
Randall?
Kev?
I want to hit you,
but I also want to kiss you.
Yeah, that's...
I get it.
Sounds like you had
some company, though, right?
Yeah, he, um...
he called to check in on me.
He was on the phone for hours.
Really? Wow.
Randall, I don't know
what to say, man.
Nothing required, man.
I knew you'd make it.
I'm gonna pass the torch.
We'll catch up soon.
Thanks, guys.
Hey. You got this, M-Cat.
I can't believe
you actually made it.
Yeah, no, it's...
You wouldn't believe
the insane night that I had.
The head of TSA
at the Seattle airport is
definitely going
on our Christmas card list.
Doesn't matter.
None of that matters.
The only thing that matters
is that I made it.
Before I left, you asked me
how this family was
gonna fit into my life.
Yeah.
This family is my life.
Uh, I quit the movie.
Yeah, no,
I don't want to take jobs
that are gonna take me
away from you.
And this--
these beautiful babies
that we're about ready to meet.
This is all I'll ever need.
I made it.
You made it.
♪ I saw you there♪
♪ That's when I knew...♪
These masks are really
pulling my ears forward.
I feel like Dumbo. You're about
ready to have twins with Dumbo.
♪ When good love shines,
I feel it, too♪
♪ Take me with you,
take me with you♪
♪ So I build a boat to sail♪
♪ I swear I'll never fail you♪
♪ Oh, we'll sail into the sun♪
♪ Take my hand and run into♪
♪ The sea of love♪
♪ And we will swim
without our clothes♪
♪ And watch the waves,
see where they'll go♪
♪ When waters rise,
they sometimes do♪
♪ I'll be with you,
I'll be with you♪
♪ So I build a boat to sail♪
♪ I swear I'll never fail you♪
♪ Oh, we'll sail into the sun♪
♪ Take my hand and run into♪
♪ The sea of love♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh♪
Kate.
I want to hold her.
I know that I said that
I didn't, but I changed my mind.
Uh, of course. Yeah.
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh♪
♪ The sea of love♪
♪ So I build a boat to sail♪
-♪ I swear I'll never fail you♪
-♪ The sea of love♪
♪ The sea of love♪
♪ The sea of love...♪
All right, Mom.
-Here's your daughter.
-Oh, um, she's gonna hold her.
Hi.
So that's what you look like.
Kate, do you...
do you mind if...
I would just like
to be alone with her.
Oh, um...
yeah.
Of course.
♪ I feel it, too♪
♪ Take me with you,
take me with you.♪
G-7?
The twins are good.
Still just the one picture,
and no new update from Kate.
Well, I'm sure
we'll hear something
-when there's something to hear.
-Yeah.
What is that?
-Hmm?
-The blobs.
The-the painting. You've been
staring at that all night.
What is that?
What's all this?
This is the best
possible solution
I could find
to try and save them.
I'm gonna go get my hair dryer.
No, Bec.
It's fine. They-they're ruined.
Really, I'm-I'm over it.
Jack...
making fun of our kids together
is our thing.
It's our one coping mechanism
against three sets
of teenage hormones.
Yeah, I know. You're right.
So, what is the deal?
They don't want to hang out
with us anymore.
It's-it's...
it's moving really fast.
You know, they-they like us
one moment, and then the next...
They're teenagers.
It's perfectly normal
that they want to
hang out with
other teenagers over us.
I know, but we only have
a few more years together
under the same roof.
Okay, a few more years
where we get to be a part
of their daily lives.
And then what?
They're gonna move out.
And forget vacations
to the cabin.
Babe, w-we're gonna
be lucky if they call us
once a week just to let us know
what's going on in their lives.
Babe, it is not
gonna be like that.
It was like that for us.
We moved out
of our parents' houses,
and we never looked back.
Okay.
You being moody I can handle,
but comparing us to our parents,
that is a bridge too far,
mister.
Jack, our family is not
ending anytime soon.
Come here. Come here.
Look at this picture.
Do you see how the colors
from their little handprints
have... have soaked
all the way down to ours?
We're all still there together.
We are, even if it doesn't look
the way that it used to.
And even when we are old fogeys
living out here
in the woods one day
like witches from
some children's fairy tale,
we're still gonna
be close to them.
Didn't realize we were
gonna be witches.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I'm gonna
let myself really go.
Oh, okay.
We will never miss a thing.
Not the little stuff,
and especially not
the big stuff.
Mm.
So we framed it,
as a... reminder
to always be close,
never miss a thing.
I know it's silly,
but I feel like...
like I'm letting down Jack
by not being there
for them today.
Like I'm-I'm not holding up
my end of the promise.
-Rebecca, you...
-No, it-it's okay.
You don't have to
make me feel better.
We never talk about this.
How you...
have to bear
Jack's death differently.
For yourself...
and for me.
And our marriage.
Thank you.
I know it's a lot.
I know I'm a lot.
Hey.
You're just the right amount.
Hi, little one.
So you're the reason
I've been skipping cold cuts
for the last nine months, huh?
You should know
that I live and die
by pastrami on rye, so...
this hasn't been easy for me.
But...
from the minute that I knew
that you were real
and I was really having you...
...I knew that I needed
to take care of you.
Even if you were never
meant to be mine.
Giving you to Toby and Kate is
the hardest thing
I have ever done.
But it might just be
the best thing I'll ever do.
So I have to say goodbye
to you now,
because there is
someone really special
waiting to say hello.
Hi.
Thank you.
Hi, sweet girl.
Hi. It's so nice to meet you.
Oh, my goodness.
Hi.
I'm your mom.
I feel like I have waited
my whole life to meet you.
I can't wait
to watch you grow up.
To French-braid your hair.
And to make
Play-Doh castles together.
And I got to be honest with you.
The world is...
it's a little nutty out there
right now, but...
no matter what, no matter what,
You will never, ever...
doubt your place in it.
And I'm really excited for you
to meet your dad.
Do you want to meet your dad?
Hey.
Do we have a baby?
We do.
Meet your daughter Hailey.
Hi there, Hailey Rose.
Hailey Rose Damon.
I love it.
Aw.
Wait, after Rose Tico
fromStar Wars, right?
Uh...
yeah, something like that.
Oh, my goodness,
look at all that hair.
What I wouldn't give.
She's like Fabio in his prime.
I know.
Oh, it's Kev.
Well,
how does it feel to be the Pearson family's newest dad?
Yeah. Man, I can't believe
I'm a dad, dude.
Congrats, Papa Bear.
-Beth says...
-I heard.
Yeah, no, I heard.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Uh, you got names?
Names? Yes.
Uh, Nicholas and Frances.
Nicholas.
Oh, man, Uncle Nicky
will be through the roof.
And, uh, Frances?
-Frances?
-That's... unique.
I know, I know.
Um, named after
Madison's grandmother.
Um, she gave me Nicky,
so we'll-we'll call her Franny.
Right on. Franny's cute.
Franny is definitely cute.
-Yeah, yeah.
Man, eight hours ago,
I was dragging some guy
out of his totaled SUV,
and now here I am a dad.
To twins.
Damn.
Yesterday, I was in New Orleans
communing with the spirit
of my birth mom.
Now I own her house.
Damn.
Yeah.
We got a lot to catch up on.
Randall, I was terrified
when I was on that plane.
I was terrified that
I wouldn't make it in time,
and I was terrified that
she would be alone,
and when I walked in that room,
man, I heard your voice,
and I, um...
Thank you. Thank you.
After everything that
we've been through recently,
you're still...
You're my brother.
Yeah.
I did say some... some pretty
horrible things to you, Randall,
and the truth is you are...
You're the best person I know.
And on my finest day,
I am simply doing a poor man's imitation of you.
Hey, man.
We both said things.
Tensions were high.
We got a lot of ground to cover.
Lot of things I didn't...
see growing up.
Hey, man.
If you really want to have
that conversation with me,
then I cannot wait
to have it with you.
And one day, when you don't have
two brand-spanking-new babies
and just went through a whole
Planes, Trains and Automobiles
adventure to get to,
we will have it.
I promise you that.
But now is not the time.
Now is the time to celebrate
your new family.
Yes.
I can't believe you told her the "MMMBop" story.
Hi.
What time does your watch say?
Um...
-9:53.
-Mm.
9:53. That's good.
I was worried maybe all the
clocks in the house were fast.
I didn't want to accuse you
of being
three hours and 53 minutes late
for no reason.
-Look, Es, I...
-One night.
I asked you for one night
to come home at 6:00
to have dinner with your son.
He was so excited for you
to eat the pizza he made you.
I wanted to make it home.
What could you be doing
in that office
that is so much
more important than us?
I'm so close
to something huge, Es.
No one has created
an efficient algorithm
to compute
the Karhunen-Loève transform.
So I had the idea
to approach the problem
by studying a cosine transform,
-and then...
-No, stop.
If I am going to forgive you,
then I need to understand why
what you are doing matters
so much to you.
So explain it to me
so I will understand.
Explain it to me like I'm...
like I'm our four-year-old son.
All right, well,
you want to move on
to something else?
No, it's-it's late.
I think I'm all gamed out.
-Okay.
Oh, God, it's Kate.
When your mother wants a picture
of Mike, what do we do?
We mail it to her.
Right. We mail it to Argentina.
She gets it a few weeks later.
What if, instead of waiting
for the mail,
she could see the photo
on a computer almost instantly?
What do you mean?
The military has created
a network of computers
around the world
that are all connected.
Soon, common people
will have them,
and if my team can optimize
a form of data compression,
they'll be able to share images.
So, you put a picture
on a computer,
and my mother across the world
sees the same picture?
Yes, and imagine if one day
it wasn't just a picture.
Imagine it was a movie.
Imagine you could talk
to someone on a screen,
like a phone call
but with video.
-Hi. Hi, sweetheart.
-Hi, Kate.
Hi, Mom.
-Hi.
I'm sorry I couldn't call
during the labor.
It got really intense in there.
-It's okay.
-But, um, she's here.
She's here. Do you want to meet your granddaughter?
Yes, I do. We do.
Oh...
my goodness.
-That's Hailey.
Wow.
See her?
-She's gorgeous.
Oh.
She's so beautiful, Kate.
Oh, my goodness.
I don't even know what to say.
Oh, my.
♪ It ain't no use
to sit and wonder why, babe♪
♪ If you don't know by now...♪
All right, you ready?
Look at this.
Look what we did.
So, here is
perfect baby number one.
And then...
proud mommy.
Hi.
-And...
professional tennis player.
-Hi.
Hi, Grandma.
Hi, Nick and Franny.
Look at those little faces.
♪ At the break of dawn...♪
You missed a spot, right there!
♪ I'll be gone...♪
Oh.
Is Toby jealous
of all that hair?
Of course.
I feel like I'm gonna
have to shave her head
just to, like,
level the playing field.
♪ It ain't no use
you callin' out my name...♪
This handsome young man
right here...
this is Nick.
Wait, Nick?
-You named him after me?
-Yeah.
M-Mostly Nic Cage,
but yeah, also you.
How about that?
Hi, Rose.
Badass Rose is coming home.
Nick, Franny...
Yeah.
-This is your cousin Hailey.
Oh, beautiful.
Aw, look at her.
My goodness.
The new Big Three.
♪ It ain't no use you turnin' on
your light, babe♪
♪ The light
that I never knowed...♪
Just squeeze
those babies' cheeks for us
and tell them how much
we love them, okay?
We will. Okay.
Okay, Mom. Say goodbye,
everybody. Bye, fam.
Love you.
-Love you, too.
-Yeah, we love you. We miss you.
♪ Goodbye's too good
a word, baby♪
♪ So I'll just say
fare thee well♪
♪ I'm thinkin'
and I'm wonderin'♪
♪ All the way down the road♪
♪ I once loved a woman♪
♪ A child, I'm told♪
♪ I gave her my heart♪
♪ But she wanted my soul♪
♪ Don't think twice♪
♪ Don't think twice,
it's all right.♪