Previously on This Is Us...
I just got six messages
from the adoption agency.
We have a match.
I free you from your
"Jerry Maguire at the U-Haul,"
what-if marriage proposal that you made.
Yeah, I don't think
I'm gonna take it back.
Your life has really been
defined by your mothers.
William told me everything he
knew about my birth mother.
I'll never know much about her.
There are things, Dr. Leigh,
that I don't feel comfortable
talking to you about.
I'm gonna make a change, and...
find a Black therapist.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
_
(HAI LAUGHING)
(BOTH SPEAK VIETNAMESE)
Oh!
(MUTED LIVELY CHATTER)
Subtitle sync and corrections by
awaqeded for www.addic7ed.com.
DR. GRADER: Three pounds heavier.
Hey, hey, you hear that, kid?
Three pounds heavier than last year.
He's still only in the 30th percentile.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means you've got a long
way to go to be average.
Randall, just try to
be supportive, okay?
Your brother's playing
football this year.
He's gonna need the extra weight.
Kev's going out for quarterback.
Well, you boys are definitely
at the age where your bodies
will start changing.
Growth spurts.
Added muscle. Facial hair.
Geez, Doc, would it kill you
to have a Consumer Reports lying around?
(JACK SCOFFS)
KATE: What is taking them so long?
Stewart and Tonya will be
at the house in an hour.
Stewart? I thought you
weren't talking to Stewart
after the big breakup.
He chose to be in my group project.
Oh.
He chose you.
- Interesting. Mm.
- (DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
- Oh.
- RANDALL: What happened
- to the candies?
- What are you, six years old, nerd?
At least I'm not built like
a six-year-old, dumb-ass.
KATE: No, you guys just act
like a bunch of six-year-olds.
- Ha-ha-ha! -Ha!
- Dad!
- Guys. Both of you.
- Come on, let's go to the car.
Shotgun!
Thanks.
Not often do I send parents
off with three teens
the exact same age going through puberty
at the exact same time.
I'm not a religious man,
but I'll pray for you.
- Good luck.
- REBECCA: Mm-hmm.
JACK: Hmm.
- (WHISPERS): Yeah.
- Mm.
DR. WILTON: I don't think of myself
as a therapist who works alone,
I think of this as a... collaboration,
like two songwriters.
We will find your positive rhythms
while minimizing any negative beats.
- Uh-huh.
- Feel what I'm saying?
Okay.
DR. HALMA: I'm a proponent
of CBT and CPT.
CBT is Cognitive Behavioral Therapy,
and CPT is Cognitive Processing Therapy.
I'm sorry, are you frozen?
No. No, I am not.
That said, this isn't about me.
You're gonna have to put in the work.
I'm just here to help you find
a deeper understanding of yourself
- (CHILD LAUGHS)
- and the loved ones around you.
I... am so sorry.
(CHUCKLES) My wife had to run out.
Downside of working from home, right?
That's okay, man. Go ahead.
Can you say hi?
(WHISPERS): Hi.
APRIL: Hi.
Oh, wow.
I got three of those.
(CHUCKLES):
Uh, this is my daughter, April.
April, this is...
I can't tell you his name
because of doctor-patient privilege.
Excuse me.
- Potential patient.
- (LAUGHS)
I don't mean to toot my own horn,
but I put my foot up in these pancakes.
Who wants some?
- Please.
- Oh, yes.
Thanks, Mom.
- Put my foot in these pancakes...
- We heard.
Yeah, I'm good with cereal.
All right, well, y'all eat up, then.
I don't want you late
for online school, okay?
That's just a bad look.
Made 'em from scratch.
Yeah, a lot of love went into them
- is all I'm saying.
- Oh, my God. Fine.
Okay.
- RANDALL: Morning.
- Morning, Dad.
How is everybody?
There's a lot of teen
attitude this morning.
Yeah, one day you hung the moon,
the next you're famine,
war and pestilence.
Hey, um...
I think I found my guy,
- to replace Dr. Leigh.
- Oh, wow. That's great.
So, did you talk
about family stuff, or...?
Just generally.
We, uh, we talked
about transracial identity.
I'm having a longer Zoom
session with him today.
But, uh, he checks all the boxes, Beth.
He's cool, smart, funny,
Black, a young father.
We got a lot in common.
- Young father?
- Hey, watch your mouth now.
- Mm, mm.
- Mm-hmm.
Hey. You barely touched the pancakes.
You refuse to use cage-free eggs.
- RANDALL: Tess, you need to eat.
- I had some yogurt. I'm good.
(SIGHS)
Ugh. That girl is killing
me three times a day.
RANDALL: Mm.
Mmm.
Damn, Beth, you put your foot up
in these pancakes.
Thank God for you, baby.
- Mm. Thank God for you.
- Mwah.
Thank God for these pancakes.
(SOFT, ELECTRONIC CHIMING)
♪
Hey.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Geez, how many workouts
are you up to a day now?
Two. Maybe two and a half. Why?
- Curious. Me learning about you.
- Ah, yes.
You know, I feel like lately
the half sessions are just me
burning through crap I got going
on with my brother, you know?
Not sure those are the muscles
you work on for that,
but I am not a professional.
Who brought those?
Those are balloons from
your mom and Miguel.
I thought you told 'em we're
not doing engaged engaged.
No, I did. I did.
I told 'em the whole thing.
But, you know, they're... old.
So...
Anyway, are you, um...
What are we doing? (CHUCKLES)
We are doing a
nontraditional engagement,
where the woman gets pregnant first
and then the man moves in with her
because of a global pandemic.
Mm. That's right. Now it's...
Now I remember. You know,
they really got to start
making Hallmark cards for
people like us. You know?
(CHUCKLES)
A-And you're-you're good with...
with where we are?
Yeah.
- You?
- Uh, yeah.
Yes.
Don't worry. These are
gluten-free and low-cal.
- But no shirt, no service.
- I'm on it.
(PHONE CHIMES)
What's going on here? (GRUNTS)
Oh, wow.
What?
Uh...
I think I just got the part.
I mean, pending a-a good
meeting with the director,
I-I got the part. (CHUCKLES)
The legal movie?
The lawyer with the glass eye?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. No, it's not...
The-the title of the movie is Glass Eye.
He's got two eyes
just like mine, made out of...
- uh...
- (CHUCKLES): I don't know
what eyes are made out of.
- But congratulations.
- This is... Thank you.
Yeah, this is great.
Um...
Although I probably should, uh,
stick to, like, just
straight-up lean chicken breast
and water from here on out.
I got to have my shirt off in the movie
for a couple of scenes, love scenes.
So I'm going straight-up
Gosling for this
or Pitt in Fight Club or something.
- I don't know. I'm not...
- (PHONE RINGING)
This is my agent.
Sorry, I have to take this.
Um, I'm sorry about this.
I'm-I'm gonna cook you dinner,
okay? I'll make dinner?
Okay?
♪
I'm nervous.
Yeah, I'm nervous, too.
But I'm nervous and I'm excited.
- What is that, like, nerve-cited?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Remember, we're just meeting
a potential birth mother.
- Right.
- All right? We're gonna get to know her.
She's gonna get to know us.
No expectations. Right?
Now, am I looking
for her and her daughter
or just Ellie?
No, just Ellie.
Someone's watching her daughter.
Whose name is Willow, by the way.
And she's eight years old,
just as a reminder.
(GASPS) Babe.
Oh, my gosh.
Which mask should I wear?
- You brought options?
- Yes.
- Uh-huh.
- This one.
- And...
- (INHALES)
Yeah.
Ugh. Flowers.
- What?
- Definitely the flowers.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I thought you would love this one.
I love it. Wrong vibe.
Okay. All right.
Okay, kiss me.
Okay, uh...
Gosh, Tobe, I want this so bad.
- (EXHALES)
- I know.
Now, are we in San
Pee-dro or San Pay-dro?
I-I don't want to come off
looking like a rube.
- I think it's Pay-dro. Yeah.
- Pay-dro.
- Pay-dro. San Pay-dro.
- Pay-dro. Yeah.
- San Pay-dro.
- ELLIE: Kate and Toby?
- Hi. (CHUCKLES)
- KATE: (GASPS) Hi! -Hi!
- Hi, I'm-I'm Ellie.
- TOBY: Hi!
Hi. (CHUCKLES)
KATE: How nice to meet you.
ELLIE: Yeah. Welcome to San Pee-dro.
TOBY (QUIETLY): Pee-dro. Damn it.
- KATE: 'Kay.
- Ha-ha!
- That is an amazing mask. (CHUCKLES)
- TOBY: Oh. (GROWLS PLAYFULLY)
Stewart chose to be in your
project for a reason, Kate.
He clearly still likes you.
You think so?
I have got snacks. Nothing healthy.
Only the fun stuff,
- including Funyuns.
- Mom.
Bagel Bites.
Stewart loves Bagel Bites.
Oh. How could I forget?
- Thanks, Mom.
- Yeah.
Hi, Randall.
- Hey.
- We're building a desert biome.
Want to see?
No, I made that in third grade.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Got it!
Hi. I brought Play-Doh
for the cacti and aquarium sand
- for the desert floor.
- Great. Come on in.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
KATE: By the way,
- I love your mask.
- Oh.
Um, my family's from Pittsburgh.
We are diehard Steelers fans.
I know. I saw it in your profile.
I wore it as an homage.
My dad is from Johnstown.
- Really?
- Yeah.
But don't tell me that
you actually named
your daughter Willow
- after...
- Willow Rosenberg. Yes.
- No way.
- Yes. Oh, I'm a huge Buffy fan.
- Huge. Yes.
- What?
- Okay. All right.
- (LAUGHS)
So can we adopt you?
Can we, Tobe? Can we...?
- You know?
- I'm free.
Is that crazy?
Okay, it's crazy. All right...
No, it's not, I just think we might
have strayed from the topic here.
Yes, sorry, sorry.
Having too much fun, okay.
Okay, so, um,
why am I placing this
child for adoption?
I married my high school sweetheart,
Willow's father,
and I lost him to cancer.
Oh.
And it was...
awful beyond awful,
so I don't want to dwell on it,
except to say that it
took me a few years
to even think about another man,
let alone go out with one,
in the middle of raising
my daughter by myself.
But all of my girlfriends
said that it was time for
me to get back out there.
So I went on Match and I met up
with this handsome stranger
and there were drinks,
a lot of drinks,
and I ended up in his bed
about five hours after
learning his name.
You must think I'm so messed up.
Not at all.
Trust me, I have thought about this.
I have thought about this
more than I have ever thought
about anything else in my whole life.
And... this baby will do better
if she is raised elsewhere.
With parents who... really want her.
(LAUGHS): And it'll make me feel
like I'm doing something right.
- (PHONE PLAYS "GHOSTBUSTERS")
- Oh.
I am so sorry. That is my mom.
She's watching Willow today,
so just one sec. Sorry.
♪ Ghostbusters! ♪
(WHISPERING): When there's something
strange in the neighborhood.
- She has "Ghostbusters." What?
- I know.
It's like... it's like she's combed
through our social media or something.
It's validating that she has
exquisite taste in pop culture,
- but we should exercise caution.
- I am so sorry.
- No, it's okay.
- My child is having a meltdown,
so, uh, I may have to wind this up
- just a little sooner than I wanted.
- KATE: Oh, no.
Like, got to call a Lyft in, like, 15.
- Oh. All right, well...
- I mean, we could take you,
- if you want, right, Tobe?
- Oh, no, you don't need to do that.
No, it's fine. Like...
- Okay, all right, then. Well,
that buys us more time. - Let's roll.
VANCE: So,
how have things been since we spoke?
All good, thanks.
I, uh... I like
that painting behind you.
Don't tell me. Uh, Kadir Nelson?
Yes. You collect him?
Uh, well, no.
Um, I mean, I've seen his stuff before.
My wife's the one
who turned me on to him.
(CLEARS THROAT) She's a big fan.
Beth's her name... my wife.
She's Black. Just so you know,
I'm married to a Black woman,
so, you know...
Randall, you know you
have absolutely nothing
to prove to me, right?
Uh... (LAUGHS)
I'm a little nervous.
I know I told you this morning
what brought me here, and I just...
This is important to me.
- I want to do this right.
- I hear you.
But this is a process.
And keep in mind, not all the
work is done here in this room.
You seem like a guy
who likes homework, so,
here's your first assignment.
Tonight, I want you
to write down a story
from your childhood... just one story.
Something that you think might
tell me something about you.
Uh, grab a notebook and keep it
handy when it comes to you.
Just something you'd like me to know.
Okay.
- Um...
- (PHONE CHIMES)
Sorry. Let me shut this down. _
Whew!
- All right, I'm all yours.
- (CLAPS HANDS)
Yeah, you've probably never
heard of the director before.
His name is Jordan Martin Foster.
He won the Jury Prize at Cannes.
Are you okay?
Yeah, fine.
Just so you know: sex scenes
couldn't be less sexy.
Okay? And I'm not even kidding.
I mean, you got crew members
standing around all over the place.
Plus, with COVID now, I don't even know
if we'll be in the same studio.
For all I know,
I'll be in Burbank somewhere,
she'll be in Culver City,
and they'll just
throw us together in post.
You got nothing to worry about.
I'm not worried about it. Let's go back.
- My feet hurt.
- I'm sorry. Excuse me.
I'm so sorry. I just wanted
to say I am a big fan.
- Oh, thank you.
- Um, Julia.
- Hi.
- Could I get a picture?
Okay.
Oh. Wow. Congratulations.
How many weeks do you have to go?
- Um, just a few months.
- Oh, lucky girl.
You just have the cute
little basketball belly.
Me? My son's a year old,
I'm still running it off.
Uh... let's get
that socially-distanced selfie, right?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- (JULIA LAUGHS, PHONE CLICKS)
- There you go. All right.
- Thanks.
- It's a good one. Thank you.
Madison! Hey, hey.
Madison? Listen,
if you're upset with me...
- I'm not.
- Okay, listen, you can come
to the filming of the love
scene if that's really
- what's bothering you.
- I am not upset about the love scene.
It seems like you're upset
about the love scene.
I'm not upset about the love scene!
I'm upset about the pancakes.
I'm upset that she
can tell I'm pregnant.
Okay, I'm-I'm upset
about a whole bunch of stuff
I'm not comfortable sharing with you
because we're basically strangers.
(SIGHS SOFTLY)
Don't follow me.
I'm walking back to the house.
Go a different way.
I'm so sorry. Could I get
another? I-I blinked.
What?
(BIRD SQUAWKING)
The oil's boiling.
_
You said we only have
to speak Vietnamese
when we are fishing.
You always get the last word
in every language.
Everything takes so long.
Fishing the fish, cooking the fish.
Let's play Go Fish.
You need to learn patience, Linh.
Preparing a meal is the way
to show someone you love them.
I learned to cook
because I want to impress
someone very special to me.
Who?
So many questions in such a little body.
Sit.
I will not tell you who I cook for,
but I will show you how I cook for her.
Her! It's a girl.
Sit.
BOY (ON TV): Hey,
- what you doing?
- MAN: Oh, just straightening up a bit.
BOY: Yeah, well, we don't go in
for that sort of stuff around here.
Huh.
So, you, uh,
didn't find anything, did you?
- Such as?
- Nothing. I mean,
- I just lost Inky's ball.
- Inky?
I love Mr. Belvedere.
Although I'm more of a
Who's the Boss? girl.
I bet you're the Brainiac that
doesn't need to do homework.
You just watch TV all
day and get all As.
I have a routine.
Snack, watch Mr. Bel,
and then do my homework.
I'm in the middle of
my routine right now.
- (DOOR OPENS)
- JACK: Hey, everybody.
REBECCA: Hey.
How was football?
- Fine.
- Fine?
Coach said we've got another
Terry Bradshaw right here.
Minus the hair loss.
- Yeah, of course.
- Obviously, Kevin.
Hey, you know what else Coach said?
Kev gets a little stronger,
he's gonna be a force.
So I'm gonna take him out in
the garage, pump a little iron.
Oh. The garage. Dad's sanctuary.
- Okay.
- Go upstairs and change, all right?
- (LAUGHS)
- What's going on here?
Study group.
Studying what?
Relax. They're fine, Jack.
Really? You're not gonna meddle?
No, no, no, no. Meddling was
so Seventh Grade Rebecca.
- This is Eighth Grade Rebecca.
- Oh.
Cool Mom Rebecca.
You know, I can monitor the
situation, but in a cool way.
- Okay. Yeah, Cool Mom.
- Cool Mom.
Cool Mom.
- Hey, babe.
- Yeah.
You really think it's okay
for Kev to be pumping iron?
I mean, teens' bones and
muscles are still developing.
Say the thing you want to say.
No. Cool Mom Rebecca doesn't meddle.
Okay. I-I got this.
Yeah, it's really cute.
He, like, has his own
little made-up language.
- (ELLIE LAUGHS)
- And everything rhymes.
It's really cute.
Oh, hey, Tobe, the sitter said
that she can't find any diapers.
Yeah, well, you bought some yesterday.
- Yeah. Yeah, I did.
- Well, where are they?
I don't know.
You brought the groceries in.
Okay.
Ugh. Come on, Tobe.
You were supposed to check the
diaper supply before we left.
No, I checked the
diaper supply yesterday
and saw that we were low
and wrote "diapers"
on the shopping list.
Right, and then I bought
the diapers that were
on the shopping list, and
you were supposed to take them
- out of the trunk.
- We wouldn't run out of diapers so fast
if we could please just buy in bulk.
I'm not gonna hoard diapers, Tobe.
Like, other people need diapers, too.
I'm not talking about buying
all of the diapers in the world,
but this kid is a human outhouse.
Maybe if we just get, like,
an extra box or two.
Okay, so it's my fault? It would
be really great, just, like,
one time if you could be like,
"My fault,"
like you took the blame
just for something.
Just like, "Hey, it was me."
I take the blame for everything.
I am this family's blame piñata! Pow!
Blame scattered on the floor.
Blame piñata.
That's good.
Thanks, it felt good
rolling off the tongue.
I'm sorry I left the diapers
in the trunk.
- I'm an idiot.
- Babe, you're not an idiot.
And we both know that,
uh, we've had our son
sit in his diaper for a
lot longer than this, so...
(LAUGHS) Yeah,
I actually think he likes it.
'Cause he's gross. (LAUGHS)
(TOBY SIGHS)
- Ready?
- Yes.
(LAUGHS)
(HIP-HOP BEAT PLAYING)
♪ Okay, you wanna,
you wanna play with me ♪
♪ But so confused,
all the things to say ♪
♪ Want to be invited to parties ♪
♪ But you can't even pronounce my name ♪
♪ You need to be up on this,
right here's where... ♪
Hey, Mr. Phillips,
I'm a they, not a she.
Told you about 17 times now,
so if you've got a problem
with that, then screw you!
♪ Gettin' lit, all of these
weekends I spend gettin' lit ♪
♪ I swear to Jesus
it's been on my list... ♪
Hey, Ms. Jennings.
When we get back to school,
don't touch my hair anymore.
Like Solange says, don't touch my hair.
Does this make you uneasy?
Does this make you uncomfortable?
Because that's how you make us feel.
- Screw you!
♪ Okay. ♪
There anything you want
to say before we do?
We did it last year after
Ms. Jennings touched my hair,
- then kept doing it to other kids.
- BETH: Tess,
if a teacher touched your hair,
you know what, you should have gone
to that teacher,
or you should have come to us.
You do not post
a profane, mocking dance video
for the world to see.
I did tell the teacher.
I said, "Please don't touch my hair."
RANDALL: And did she stop?
She stopped with me.
But not with all the
other Black students.
Well, Tess, the other
students aren't your problem.
Silence in the face of injustice
is complicity with the oppressor.
Okay, the teachers
didn't get the message
when we asked nicely, but they
definitely got the message now.
BETH: Hey.
Check the attitude, okay, Tess?
Now, this Alex,
did she make you do this?
Alex is not a she. They're a they.
Fine. They.
No one made me do anything.
You tell me to be myself.
Well, this is me now, guys.
Have you seen what's
going on in the world?
I'm done waiting to figure out who I am.
I'm done being the prissy,
quiet little girl
you raised in the
straight, white suburbs
surrounded by straight, white people.
This is who I want to be.
This is who I am.
Go to your room, Tess.
This'll go right here.
Stewart, we can stop pretending
why you picked my study group.
I miss you, too.
I picked your group
because I like deserts.
This is where the action is.
Snakes, Gila monsters,
scorpions.
(TV PLAYING QUIETLY)
(LIPS SMACK)
It's crazy.
This tastes just like root beer.
Want to try?
I should really get to my homework.
That's an angry pour.
Grazie.
What's that?
It's a journal for Dr. Vance.
Supposed to write down a story
about my childhood.
Can only imagine what Tess is
gonna write about us someday.
She's lashing out.
She should know better.
The Internet has a long memory.
We taught her to know better, Randall.
Yeah. Yeah, we did.
As a parent, I agree with you.
She did not go about this the right way,
but... and just stay with me here...
part of me is kind of proud of her.
Oh. (LAUGHS)
If something bothered
me when I was her age,
I swallowed it.
I've always been worried
that Tess was like me.
You know, internal. Anxious.
But all of a sudden,
she's coming into her own.
She's not afraid of who she is.
She's not gonna have to go
see a therapist at 40
to figure that out.
- I know. And I hear you.
- Mm-hmm.
But they are teenagers now, husband.
- Okay?
- Mm-hmm.
This is what we have been training for.
- (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
- There has got to be consequences
for what she's done. All right?
And strong parenting is not
playing good cop, bad cop.
We have to be on the same page.
Starting now.
So you want me to go talk to her?
Ding, ding, ding.
- TOBY: No, just pull it once.
- ELLIE: Maybe. No. Hold on.
- TOBY: Just pull it once. Yeah.
- ELLIE: I'm sorry. (LAUGHS)
- There you go. (LAUGHS)
- (KATE LAUGHS)
- Thank you for the ride. This was fun.
- (TOBY CLEARS THROAT)
Oh, i-i-it was. Yeah.
Uh...
and I'm sorry if our arguing
made you feel uncomfortable.
I mean, we actually
get along very well, so...
Yeah, which works out good,
'cause we're married.
(KATE AND ELLIE LAUGH)
Well, Doug... my husband...
he used to overbuy condiments.
It was as if he lived in perpetual fear
of running out of mustard.
(CHUCKLES): It drove me nuts,
and we fought about it constantly.
- Mustard-gate. Ketchup-gate. Mayo-gate.
- (CHUCKLES)
Mayo-gate was, uh,
it was especially bad. (LAUGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
I think you can tell a lot about
a couple by how they fight.
How they recover.
I have a strong feeling about you guys.
Thanks for coming
all the way to San Pedro.
- Yeah.
- Oh, of course. Our pleasure.
Yeah, love San Pedro.
(LAUGHING): "We love San Pedro."
Okay, bye.
See you.
Bye.
KEVIN: Hey. How you feeling?
Fine. Soaked my feet.
Oh, good. Good.
- So, I-I didn't mean to, uh...
- Don't.
You did nothing wrong.
I said something. I don't...
Was it about the movie
or the babies? Uh...
I had an eating disorder, Kevin.
I'm not sure how much you know,
but I've been struggling
with eating issues
for as long as I can remember,
and, um...
then comes this pregnancy.
You know why that ultrasound
picture is on the fridge
and not on a bulletin board
or a bathroom mirror?
I keep that there
to remind me to eat.
To eat food, Kev.
To eat food to keep our babies healthy.
Do you know when I go to the doctor,
the first thing they do is weigh me?
And they announce the number out loud,
and I have to remind myself
to act proud that I've put on two pounds
when for most of my adult life,
news like that would
just make me spiral.
It's hard to adjust.
I didn't know.
Of course you didn't.
I've been hiding a lot
of myself from you.
This whole thing isn't normal, Kev,
as much as we pretend it is.
Everything came backwards here,
and I'm all over the place.
Insecurities running wild,
and-and you're walking around
like an Olympic swimmer
most of the time.
I'm sorry.
I'm fine.
I love our babies.
I'm just dealing with a lot right now.
It's on me.
All right. (SIGHS)
You ready?
(AUSTRIAN ACCENT): I am Hans.
(AUSTRIAN ACCENT): And I am Franz.
BOTH: And we want to pump you up!
(BOTH LAUGH)
- (REGULAR VOICE): Okay. Let's, uh...
- (WEIGHT SCRAPES)
You know, let's start with just the bar.
'Cause, you know, you're still
developing and everything.
Come on, man, throw in some lead.
No, Kev, come on.
The bar is-is plenty heavy.
All right? But first,
what I want you to do is,
you got to warm up.
Right? We got to loosen things up.
Pull your arm through.
Warm your shoulders up.
There you go. Yeah.
Go the other arm. All right.
Go across. Go across.
- (INHALES, EXHALES FORCEFULLY)
- (EXHALES FORCEFULLY)
(JACK LAUGHS)
All right, here we go.
- (KNUCKLES CRACK)
- (GRUNTS)
Knuckle popping is optional.
- (KNUCKLES CRACK)
- All right.
KATE: Stewart's a desert groupie, Mom.
That's why he wanted to be
in our study project.
- It wasn't to be with me.
- REBECCA: Oh.
I see.
I feel like an idiot.
No, don't.
Following your heart
is a real strength, Kate.
Yeah, sometimes you end up getting hurt,
but most of the time,
it'll all work out.
I know it's not the cool thing to say,
but I'm really proud of you,
and I love you.
TOBY: All right.
Emergency diaper stash restocked.
(KATE LAUGHS)
- Ah...
- What's so funny?
Oh, uh, Ellie said the Buffy
episode "Hush" was on, so...
Babe, "Hush"?
The one where everyone in Sunnydale
loses the ability to talk?
Do not insult me. I know the episode.
- Please.
- Excuse me.
But c-could we just not
- text her as much, please?
- She texted me.
Come on. Just admit, it went well.
And could you just be a little excited
- about that?
- Not really.
This baby stuff wasn't
that easy the first time.
You know, with this, we're dealing
with a 33-year-old single mother
who could, literally, at any moment,
change her mind about us.
So instead of asking me
to be more excited,
could maybe you... you try
to be a little more terrified?
(SIGHS) Okay.
You know what, she does smile
a lot when she rubs her belly.
Which is better than
the opposite, obviously,
but I don't know, I clocked it.
- Oh, babe.
- See? Thank you.
Thank... no, that makes me feel better.
Thank you for registering
an acceptable level of terror.
- Mm.
- I appreciate it.
Yeah, okay, you're welcome.
She did say that her favorite
Star Wars character
was Babu Frik.
That's a fresh take. Respect.
And did you see the look
on her face when she noticed
that we had forgotten
the diapers in the car?
That was the look of a woman
who is falling hard for us.
- Babe.
- Yeah. Those are good things.
- Those are good things.
- Okay, well, thank you
for registering a, you know, an
acceptable level of excitement.
Thank you.
Also, I, um, bought the diapers,
for the record.
- You left 'em in the trunk.
- (LAUGHS): Uh...
Uh, excuse me.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
RANDALL: "Come in."
"Oh, thanks, daughter,
don't-don't mind if I do."
(SIGHS)
"Silence in the face of inequality
is complicity with the oppressor."
- Ginetta Sagan.
- You caught that.
I catch everything, daughter.
There's a right way and a wrong way
to get your point across.
Even loudly, if need be.
And this was the wrong way.
And it's not you.
Telling adults to screw
themself on the Internet?
- That's not you.
- It is me.
It's not.
That is not the person
who made my life somersault.
- It's an old reference.
- I remember.
We're taking your phone
away for six weeks.
What? What if I'm out?
You won't be, 'cause you're
grounded for six weeks, too.
Fascist! This is bull...
You finish that sentence,
tack on three more weeks.
Good choice.
God.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Did she call you a fascist?
Yeah, hon. I believe she did.
What you want to do is,
you line your thumbs up, okay?
Make sure that bar is nice and center.
Wrap them around the bar.
Very important.
Thumb around the bar. Important.
Come on.
- Come on.
- (EXHALES SHARPLY)
Nice, Kev. You're doing great.
Last one, Kev. Last one. Here we go.
Push it, push it, push it.
Push it.
Work that chest.
Push. Push.
Push. Push, push, push, push,
push, push, push. Yeah, hey.
- All right, let's pull this up.
- No, don't touch it.
What's it, too heavy?
I could take some weight off.
- No, I got it.
- Well, come on. Man up.
- (EXHALES)
- JACK: Come on, Kev, you're good.
A couple more.
(EXHALES)
Good.
(CHUCKLES): Look at you.
You're a monster.
I did it.
Hey, look, Kev.
You put your mind to it,
you can accomplish anything.
Okay?
I'm playing a trial lawyer.
In the movie I-I play a trial lawyer.
Let me ask you a question.
Why does a trial lawyer
need to be ripped?
I don't know.
He doesn't.
(EXHALES)
I count calories, too, Madison.
And I panic inside if I don't get
a second workout in every single day.
And I prefer sweating in a dingy garage
than going to some
celebrity gym because...
(SIGHS)
Oh, God, so many reasons, actually.
This one's stronger, right here.
Put your hand right there. Strong...
Eight, nine,
ten.
Switch it up.
Flex that!
At the top.
Yeah, you did it!
- (LAUGHS)
- My boy's gonna be a beast.
And as an actor,
it just became my currency.
I actually... got famous...
...by taking my shirt off.
(SIGHS) I'm getting older
and it's getting harder.
And I'm not drinking anymore,
which is my other addiction,
so I just come in here and I just...
I channel all of that here,
and it's, uh...
...not exactly healthy.
I got stuff, too, Madison.
I got a lot of stuff.
Including stuff with my brother
that I still have to work out.
And I...
I lay in bed sometimes and I, um...
...I just stare at the
ceiling and I worry.
(SIGHS)
I worry that I'm gonna pass all
that on to my kids, you know?
All that... my unhealthy stuff.
Me, too.
You know, I suppose being parents
is gonna be hard enough on its own,
without us walking around trying to be
polite strangers in front of each other.
I mean, I had the greatest,
most connected parents
you can imagine,
and they missed so much.
(EXHALES)
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
(TV PLAYING INDISTINCTLY)
It's crazy. This tastes
just like root beer.
Want to try?
I should really get to my homework.
I always wondered what it would be like
to kiss someone like you.
♪
(EXHALES) Sorry I was so
preoccupied with Kate's project,
I didn't even get to ask
you how your day was.
- It w... it was good.
- Yeah?
Tonya seems very nice.
Yeah. Night, Mom.
Madison, I'm an alcoholic
and I'm a workout addict
with daddy issues.
Also, sometimes I get foot corns,
and when that baby
flares up in the summer,
I've been known to wear
shoes and socks at the beach.
It's bulimia,
my eating disorder.
Um, it almost killed me when I was 17.
I have a handle on it,
but even now, sometimes,
my daily state of mind
is still determined by my weight.
Also,
I am obsessed with the show Outlander.
(WHISPERS): I've gone to conventions.
No.
- Yeah.
- You're one of those people?
- Yeah. I'm one of those people.
- (EXHALES)
♪
(CLICKING RAPIDLY)
- Hey, Grandpa.
- (TIMER DINGS)
The woman?
The one you were trying
to impress with your cooking?
Is she the woman in all
the pictures around here?
So many questions in such a little body.
Linh, it's the woman
in all the pictures.
I knew it.
Subtitle sync and corrections by
awaqeded for www.addic7ed.com.