Previously on "Better Call Saul"...
- Long story short...
- [CELLPHONE BEEPS]
I am not crazy.
WOMAN: Jimmy McGill
understands he broke the law.
He's more than ready
to face the consequences.
I'll be taking a brief
sabbatical from the law.
MIKE: You take my money,
it comes out clean.
LYDIA: I have you down
as a logistics consultant.
Security consultant would be better.
- Mesa Verde can wait.
- It's not Mesa Verde.
It's Newpoint. And if I mess this up,
it's a former client.
HECTOR: I want a legitimate business
to get my stuff over the border.
My father is a simple man.
I don't trust him.
From now on, there will be only
one route for our product.
[GAGGING, CHOKING]
Call 911.
SAUL: If I had to do it all over again,
I would do some things differently.
You've never mattered
all that much to me.
[VOICE BREAKING] My brother is sick!
You're not gonna do anything, are you?
You want me to retire
over this? Insurance?!
That's the straw that broke
the camel's back.
Howard, I'm fine!
This is not what fine looks like.
♪♪
[THE INK SPOTS' "WE THREE" PLAYS]
♪ We three ♪
- ♪ We're all alone ♪
- [DISHES CLINKING]
♪ Living in a memory ♪
♪ My echo, my shadow, and me ♪
♪ We three ♪
♪ We're not a crowd ♪
♪ We're not even company ♪
♪ My echo, my shadow, and me ♪
♪♪
Gene.
Gene?
- Let's get him on some oxygen.
- ♪ What good is the moonlight? ♪
- ♪ The silvery moonlight ♪
- [OXYGEN HISSING]
♪ That shines above? ♪
♪ I walk with my shadow ♪
♪ I talk with my echo ♪
♪ But where is the one I love? ♪
♪ We three ♪
♪ We'll wait for you ♪
♪ Even 'til eternity ♪
♪ My echo ♪
- ♪ My shadow and me ♪
- [BALL SQUEAKING]
♪♪
We three, we're all alone.
- Seem like we're living in a memory.
- Flat as you can.
Take a deep breath.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
- That's my echo...
- [MACHINE WHIRS]
...my shadow, and me.
[MONITORS BEEPING]
We three, we ain't no crowd.
- Fact is, we ain't even company.
- [POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
[SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
That's my echo, my shadow, and me.
[BEEPING CONTINUES]
♪ We three ♪
Mr. Takavic, how you feeling?
- Uh... good. Yes.
- Oh.
Well, it's good news. You were right.
It's not a heart attack.
In fact, everything
I can see here looks good.
Your blood pressure's a little high,
but that's understandable
under the circumstances.
- ♪ My shadow ♪
- Headline here is... false alarm.
♪ And me ♪
[PATIENT COUGHING]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
- [DOOR SLIDES OPEN]
- WOMAN: Mr. Takavic?
Mr. Takavic, sir?
I'm so sorry. Would you mind?
I have a taxi coming.
It'll just take a moment.
[DOOR SLIDES CLOSE]
Can I have another look
at your driver's license?
Uh-huh.
[BAG RUSTLING]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[BABY CRIES IN DISTANCE]
Great.
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[GROANS]
- [SIGHS]
For some reason,
this computer keeps kicking this back.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
And this is your current address?
Uh-huh.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Can I have your
Social Security Number again?
531...
531.
That's the Pacific Northwest, right?
Y-Yeah.
I got a cousin who moved to Tacoma.
It's supposed to be beautiful up there.
Yeah.
It's, um...
beautiful.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You got a taxi. [CHUCKLES]
Go ahead. 531.
- 008...
- [KEYBOARD CLACKING]
...7...
[KEYBOARD CLACKS]
- ...1...
- [KEYBOARD CLACKS]
...4.
[KEYBOARD CLACKS]
Okay. That's 531008714?
Uh-huh.
[SIREN WAILS IN DISTANCE]
That's really...
odd.
I've never seen this before.
[SIGHS]
Oh, wait.
Oh, my God. [SIGHS]
I typed the letter "O" instead of a zero.
[CHUCKLES]
I can't believe how stupid.
- I think it's...
- Yeah, it's going through now.
So it's okay?
[CHUCKLES, SIGHS]
I'm so sorry.
[SIGHS]
- So, I can...
Have a good night.
I'm sorry for keeping you.
- [DOOR SLIDES OPEN]
- Oh, hold on!
Don't forget this.
[DOOR SLIDES SHUT]
Stay warm.
You too.
[DOOR CREAKS]
- [TAXI DOOR SQUEAKS SHUT]
- Cottonwood Mall, please.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SNIFFLES]
[SIGHS]
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
[BAG RUSTLES]
It's... It's a green light.
[ENGINE REVS]
Uh, you know what?
I'll just get out here.
Excuse me. This is good.
I'll get out here.
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
[MONEY RUSTLING]
Great. Thanks.
- [TAXI DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
- [DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
♪♪
[FIRE CRACKLING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING, DOG BARKS IN DISTANCE]
[VEHICLE PASSES]
[EXHALING HEAVILY]
[OSCAR PETERSON'S "THE SHADOW
OF YOUR SMILE" PLAYS]
♪♪
[BUBBLE POPS]
[LIGHT THUNK ON THE DOOR]
♪♪
[DOOR CREAKS]
[NEWSPAPER RUSTLES]
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
♪♪
[SPOON CLATTERS]
[KIM CLEARS THROAT]
[COFFEE PERCOLATING]
♪♪
[CELLPHONE VIBRATING]
[CELLPHONE BEEPS]
♪♪
Hey.
- I'll trade ya.
- Mm.
- [BAG RUSTLES]
- [TELEPHONE RINGING]
Let it go.
If it's important,
they'll leave a message.
[RINGING CONTINUES]
You've reached Kim Wexler.
Please leave a message.
[ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS]
Uh, Kim, it's Howard.
I'm trying to reach Jimmy.
If you would please let him know.
I really need to talk to him.
It's Chuck.
♪♪
[TIRES SCREECH]
[CAR DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
♪♪
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
Jimmy, don't.
♪♪
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[VEHICLE DOOR CLOSES]
[ELECTRICITY BUZZING]
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
[METAL CLANGING]
Excuse me, would you?
Yes.
[SIGHS]
So?
He says it started in the living room.
Somehow one of the lanterns
was knocked over.
And then...
the inspector says it was over fast...
smoke inhalation.
So he didn't suffer.
Yeah. They're gonna say that.
[SIGHS]
Did you see the backyard?
His microwave, his stereo,
his, uh, the lights, dishwasher,
all... all the kitchen stuff.
Everything electric is back there.
The firemen didn't do that.
He did that.
[SIGHS]
I saw him five days ago.
He was listening to jazz.
All the lights worked.
He was himself.
Something must have happened.
Something made him relapse.
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
I think we should go home, Jimmy.
Okay?
Come on.
Let's just go home.
[SNIFFLES]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[TOLL BOOTH BEEPS]
[GRUNTS]
Hmm.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
- Hey, Carl.
- Hey, Mike.
[KEYS JINGLE]
Here you go.
So, this is it, huh?
Yeah.
Looks that way.
You take it easy.
So, uh, the boss said
he's gonna want the windbreaker.
[CHUCKLES]
Of course he does.
Take care, Mike.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- Pop-pop!
- Yeah?
Make it go.
What's wrong with it?
You're standing on it.
I don't think so.
Look down.
You're standing on it!
Really?
[GIGGLES]
- Hey.
- MIKE: Hey.
[GIGGLES]
- You two having fun?
Five more minutes.
- Please!
- Five more minutes, but that's it.
- Hey, baby.
- Thank you.
Is that the soaker hose you two made?
Oh, yeah.
I can pick her up the rest
of the week if you want.
Are you sure? What about your new job?
Oh, I make my own hours.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Must be nice.
- Well, since you're offering.
- Well, good.
Thanks, Mike.
[VEHICLE DEPARTING]
Hmm.
...with the Isotopes capturing the title.
The pitch on the outside a cold strike.
2-1 to the right-hand-batting
McDonald, though he doesn't...
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
He turns back to the umpire.
Keith McDonald actually played for Iowa
and before was
a long-time member of Memphis.
One for seven on the new campaign.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Second. Nobody out,
a 1-0 game, the pitch.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
...through the right side of...
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
...hurdle the baseball on
its way through the infield.
Otherwise, perhaps, it might've
had a chance to take...
♪♪
[TELEPHONE DIALING]
Yes.
Las Cruces for Madrigal Intermodal.
M-a-d-r-i-g-a-l.
Yes.
♪♪
Uh-huh. Yeah.
And would you have an address for that?
[GURGLING SINK]
Jimmy?
It's Howard.
I think you should talk to him.
- Howard.
- HOWARD: Jimmy.
I'm so sorry to bother you with this.
The thing is, we wanted
to get Chuck's obituary into
the paper before the service,
but I'd really like to run it by you,
if that's okay.
[SIGHS]
Go ahead.
Great.
Okay.
Charles Lindbergh McGill,
a towering figure
in the Albuquerque legal community
who built one of the leading
law firms in the southwest,
was taken from this world
tragically and suddenly last week.
Son of Ruth and Willard McGill,
Charles was born and raised
in Cicero, Illinois, outside Chicago.
Charles graduated valedictorian
from Francis Xavier High School
at the age of 14,
making him the youngest graduate
in the history of that school.
Um...
[PAPERS RUSTLING]
In his undergraduate years at
the University of Pennsylvania,
Charles led the debate team
to national championship
three years running
and won the Larkin Prize.
He was Editor-in-Chief of the Law Review
and won the first-year
Moot Court competition at Georgetown Law,
where he went on to graduate
magna cum laude.
After clerking at both
the Delaware Court of Chancery
and the United States Court of
Appeals for the Tenth Circuit,
Charles joined
George Hamlin's solo practice
on Central Avenue
in downtown Albuquerque.
Over the course of 23 years,
the two men built
what became known as Hamlin Hamlin McGill
into a nationally recognized firm.
Charles made his mark
in many areas of the law.
Early in his career,
he excelled in criminal law,
famously arguing and winning
the precedent-setting case
of State v. Gonzalez.
No matter the case, Charles was known
for his precise, clear arguments
and his profound devotion
to the highest ideals of the law.
Charles was also active in the community,
championing education
for the underserved.
He was on the boards
of many New Mexico charities
and a founding member of both
the Southwest Coalition
for Better Schools
and the Native People's
Education Counsel.
Charles is survived by his former wife,
concert violinist Rebecca Bois,
and younger brother, James McGill,
who followed in Charles' footsteps...
Then there's information
about the memorial service,
the date, the time, and all that.
[CLEARS THROAT]
So, uh, that is what I have.
Jimmy?
It's me, Howard. Sounds good.
Oh. Jimmy's okay with it?
He likes it, Howard.
You should go ahead with it.
Well, all right.
Uh, thank him for me.
Uh, and if you need anything,
let me know.
- Yeah. I will.
- See you Sunday.
Yeah. See you Sunday.
[TELEPHONE BEEPS, PHONE THUDS]
[CORK SQUEAKS]
[LIQUID POURING]
[SIGHS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
[ENGINE RUMBLING]
EMS 16, be advised
we have one adult male...
WOMAN: Does he have a history
of cardiac issues?
NACHO: Yeah.
Copy that.
And was he taking any medications?
He took these.
Thanks.
We're headed to Lovelace
if you'd like to follow.
[SIREN WAILING]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[DIALING]
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
Don Juan.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
♪♪
- [CELLPHONE BEEPS]
- Juan Bolsa wants to see you.
♪♪
You drive.
[CONVERSATION IN SPANISH]
♪♪
[CONVERSATION CONTINUES]
[SNIFFLES]
[CONVERSATION STOPS]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACH]
[SNAPS FINGERS]
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
_
Ignacio.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
_
Gustavo.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[WINGS FLUTTERING]
[VEHICLE DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
♪♪
[WATER SPLASHES]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
♪♪
[ENGINE STARTS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
What's up?
It's busted again.
It's just the chain.
You want me to do it,
or you want to try it yourself?
[SIGHS, CHUCKLES]
Okay.
This is the last time, so watch.
All right.
So, you take this,
give it a little play, right?
Wrap it there.
Loop it around the big gear, yeah?
And then...
- That's all there is to it.
- Okay.
And?
Thanks, Dad.
Make sure Mom knows where you are.
[BELL RINGS]
[IGNITION CLICKING]
[SIGHS]
[CLICKING CONTINUES]
[CELLPHONE BEEPING]
[DIALING]
Hi, Denise.
Yeah. It's Barry.
Uh, listen, could you let Mr. Eglin know
I'm gonna be late this morning?
I might miss the staff meeting.
No, no. Car trouble.
It's probably just a dead battery.
[CHUCKLING] Yeah, I know. I know.
It's practically brand-new.
Okay. Thanks.
[CELLPHONE BEEPS]
[BRIEFCASE CLOSES, DASHBOARD OPENS]
[SIGHING]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
WOMAN: Line 2.
MAN: Oh, yeah. I do.
I have those reporter numbers for you.
Will you hang on one second?
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[FAX MACHINE WHIRRING]
You want to pick up 2?
[CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE]
I'll go ahead and take the copy for you.
MAN: Bruce had the speed.
He could kick you
before you saw him move.
You ever watched the Liston fight?
All right, we're talking
about what? Boxing?
'Cause that's something else.
No, we're talking about a street fight.
Street fight?
Great. So, Bruce can kick.
No, we're not talking about
a movie fight.
We're talking about weight.
We're talking about reach.
Boxing is a sport.
Martial arts is life and death.
Look, I don't care how fast you are.
Muhammad Ali hits you, you're going down.
- That's a fact.
- Oh, if he hits you.
Bruce Lee... he knows the anatomy.
He's got the moves.
He's gonna find an opening.
Without power, the...
the opening doesn't mean squat.
How much does he weigh?
I don't know. Maybe a buck-30.
Ali was the heavyweight champ.
He's got at least 100 pounds on Lee.
Bruce feints for Ali's head,
but he goes low
and he sweeps him to the deck.
Ali goes down hard.
- It's all over.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Does he have a gun?
- I'm sorry?
Does Bruce Lee have a gun?
Because if he doesn't,
it's Ali in three minutes or less.
See? That's what I'm saying.
That's what I'm s...
Hey, hold on. Wait. Wait.
Did you sign, uh, Tina's birthday card?
- No.
- Would you mind?
Not at all.
You're way out of line on this,
I'm telling you.
All I'm saying is, if Lee tried
to sweep Ali's legs,
he'll just sidestep.
Ali was fast for his size, yes,
but if he gets hit with a low kick,
he's not gonna know what to do.
Oh, I know what he'll do.
He'll do just fine.
You're nuts.
- Thanks.
- Yep.
Look, Bruce was a brawler, okay?
He gets in quick...
[MACHINERY WHIRRING, BEEPING]
[INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT OVER P.A.]
[BREAKESTRA'S
"DARK CLOUDS RAIN SOUL" PLAYS]
♪♪
[MACHINERY WHIRRING]
[VEHICLE BEEPING]
♪♪
[WHISTLES]
[INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT OVER P.A.]
Uh, yeah?
Ramirez.
- Team leader.
- Yes, sir.
So, Ramirez,
what do you think you're up to?
We're just filling an order.
Something wrong?
May I ask why none of your guys
are wearing a lift belt?
Lift belt.
Oh, we... we don't usually...
Stop what you're doing.
You go to the equipment room.
You get lift belts and gloves.
You use them.
Rules are rules. Got me?
Sure. Sure. Okay.
On the double.
Hey, hold up!
Shut it down.
Shut it down!
[SCANNER BEEPING]
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
Uh, excuse me.
I think this belongs to you.
Oh, my God.
[CHUCKLES]
Thank you.
Where did you find it?
I need to talk to your manager.
I waltz through security
with someone else's I.D.
Nobody gives me a second look.
When the rightful owner shows up,
there's no facility-wide badge check.
I find access doors
left unlocked or propped open,
passwords written on Post-it notes.
Warehouse workers are using pen and paper
instead of electronic inventory devices,
which leaves you wide open to pilfering.
You got duplicate
routing numbers on cargo,
surveillance-camera blind spots
on the north
and the east side of the floor,
inventory documents
that are going into the trash
instead of being shredded, not to mention
loading equipment being driven
at unsafe speeds and crews...
- Wait. Wait.
- ...disregarding safe...
Wait. Hold on. Hold on.
Who are you, exactly?
Ehrmantraut.
Security consultant.
All due respect,
I don't know anything about
a security consultant.
Well, you wouldn't, would you?
Maybe you best call corporate.
Try Lydia Rodarte-Quayle.
[GABRIEL FAURÉ "SICILIENNE" PLAYS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
♪♪
Truly sorry, Jimmy.
Thank you, Cliff. Appreciate that.
♪♪
Hey. He was a hell of a lawyer.
Yes, he was.
♪♪
Jimmy...
we're going to miss him so much.
Thank you, Brenda.
♪♪
I'm sorry for your loss.
Thanks, Brian.
♪♪
MAN: Jimmy, I'm so sorry.
Oh. Well, thanks. Appreciate that.
♪♪
[SOBBING]
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
[GEARSHIFT CLICKS, ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
I-I think I owe you
the truth about Chuck.
Those lanterns.
He was living in that house
without electricity
for the better part of two years.
He knew how to use those lanterns.
He was careful. I saw it.
I know you did, too.
There was never a problem.
I know it's a terrible thing to...
I don't think what happened
was an accident.
You probably heard
Chuck was retiring from HHM.
But that's not the truth.
The truth is
- that we had a disagreement...
and I pushed him out.
I made him go.
Chuck was sick for years.
And after the bar hearing...
The bar hearing
had nothing to do with it.
Okay.
The fact is, he started
getting better after that.
He took more of an interest in the firm.
He came to work.
We could leave the lights on.
He was improving until
the thing with the insurance.
So, I-it wasn't the bar hearing.
The insurance...?
It was a ridiculous thing.
I should've just let it go.
I mean, God knows
he's done enough for me.
But he kept pushing.
And I, um... I got my back up.
What about the insurance?
It was, uh, our malpractice insurance.
They found out about Chuck's condition,
raised our rates.
Chuck went ballistic.
He wanted to go to war.
I drew a line.
He wouldn't back down.
So I forced him out.
It never occurred to me
that I could hurt him.
He always seemed so strong.
But he wasn't.
I think he did what he did because of me.
Well, Howard, I guess
that's your cross to bear.
[FISHTANK BUBBLING]
Look at her go. [CHUCKLES]
So, I'm gonna make some coffee.
Anybody want some?
[COFFEEMAKER CLATTERING]
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[SIGHS]
[WHISTLING]