Previously on "Better Call Saul"...
I actually have the number of a shrink.
I'm already seeing someone.
I decide what he deserves.
I will get my law license back.
My partner and I will get a new office.
I have tons of Mesa Verde to catch up on.
You have work. I have work.
It's all good.
I don't know
what to tell you, Paige.
I'm sorry.
It'll never happen again.
It's impossible?
Difficult. Not quite impossible.
Give me your money.
Back in the day,
they would have known not to roll me.
Here you go.
Are you sure about these?
The pool's up to $200.
I've made my choices.
Well... Confidence.
An admirable trait.
Clara.
Hey, Jimmy.
- What do you got for me?
- I'm stuck
on Documentary Short Subject.
Mm. Yeah. Just go with your gut.
"Howards End" all the way down, huh?
I just love Emma Thompson.
Who doesn't?
She's so pragmatic.
Yeah, well, fingers crossed.
Hey, hey. Hey.
How'd we do?
This is everything from two.
And I even got Chloe to throw in.
Many have tried to argue with Kim Wexler.
All have failed.
I'm headed up to four. You got anything?
Yep.
And I'll do three.
Already done.
You know, you're making
the rest of us look bad.
If you wouldn't stop
at every cubicle to chat...
It's called being friendly.
It's great for morale.
It is great for wasting time.
- That, too.
- Okay.
It's... So, discovery for Cordero
is coming this afternoon,
so you might want to kick it up a bit.
Wow.
- Congratulations.
- He really did it.
- What?
- Isaacson.
- The case.
- I don't...
Isaacson vs. Vakarian Holdings, Inc.
We've been assembling binders for months.
I've been kind of slammed
with the Oscar pool,
in case you weren't paying attention.
Right. Sorry. I'll try harder.
So, this guy, Isaacson...
he dies of a heart attack.
- Mm-hmm.
- And his family they're our clients...
sort through his financials, you know,
looking to track down his assets.
Lo and behold, they find some old shares
in this company he invested in
like 20 years back.
Family tracks down the CFO,
looking to cash out,
but he tells them, "Hmm,
that corporation's been dissolved."
Isaacson's shares are worthless.
- Whoa.
- Right?
But Chuck does some digging,
and it turns out
they formed a new corporation
that's virtually identical
to the old corp Isaacson invested in.
It's the same officers,
same structure, everything.
- Ah.
- Right?
So, Chuck finds exemption 4
in Leannais vs. Cincinnati,
- which is compl...
- Okay. Okay. Yeah, listen.
I appreciate the effort,
but can you just big-picture it for me?
I am.
Chuck won a case
that Howard thought was unwinnable
using only the power of obscure case law.
That's... good.
Yeah, very.
Congratulations, Mr. McGill.
- Jimmy.
- Chuck.
- Big day, huh?
- Yeah.
Thanks, uh...
- Kim. Wexler.
- Of course.
- You're one of our law students?
- Yes.
- I'm in my third year at UNM...
- Ah.
...thanks to HHM.
- How's it going?
- Very well. Thank you.
And congratulations again on Isaacson.
Well...
I'm sure that you considered it.
I just wanted to ask.
Vakarian Holdings, Inc.,
would have been liable
under the "continuing
enterprise" exception,
- as well, right?
- That's right.
Yeah, we looked into that.
What was the case law on that?
- Uh, Garcia vs. Coe Manufacturing.
- Mm-hmm.
Sounds like it was Isaacson v. Chuck
handing him his butt on a platter, huh?
Well, yeah, but Isaacson is our client.
Oh, really? Okay.
Well, the... the other guys' butts, then.
Yeah, served on platters.
That's right. Thanks, Jimmy.
Hail the conquering hero.
Thanks, Howard.
I hate to interrupt,
but there's a "Mr. Bushmills"
waiting in my office.
Mmm.
Kim. Jimmy.
Congratulations.
That'll be you soon.
Yep.
Kay. See ya later, Jimmy.
See ya.
Ben, what you got for me?
There's your winner.
You think Pacino's gonna "hoo-ah" his way
to Oscar glory, huh?
Last call for ballots.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
With respect
to the zoning committee,
we maintain that the Mesa Verde statue
should be exempt
from sign code restrictions
on size and location
because it is a work of art.
Specifically, its function extends
beyond furthering the company's
economic interests,
which distinguishes it
from commercial speech
under legal precedent.
Um, Viola, can you look up
the relevant case law here for me?
I'm, uh... I think it is maybe...
uh, U.S. v. United Foods.
Yeah.
Good morning.
Jimmy. Morning!
Oh. Good morning.
I'm just... just making the O.J.
I see that.
I didn't hear you come to bed.
I was up late
justifying a giant horse statue
to the Park City zoning commission.
How big we talking?
"I'm definitely overcompensating
for some other shortcoming" big.
Your hours pretty much set now?
Yeah.
Weekdays 9:00 to 4:00, the busy time.
Oh, yeah?
It's dead, Kim.
It's deader than disco.
Mm. Sorry.
Does that mean you were able to schedule
an appointment with the therapist?
I decided not to go.
Oh.
Um... okay.
I thought you already decided to go.
I know, and I did.
But then I... time went by,
and I kind of calmed down
and realized it's just...
it's just not for me.
Why not?
It's just not.
I don't think that navel-gazing
is gonna get me where I need to be.
Yeah, but how do you know...
Unless I try?
It just doesn't feel right.
I need to be moving forward, you know?
And now I got this job,
and I'm kind of on a path.
And, uh
Just wanna give this a try.
Is that okay?
Sure.
Yeah. Of course, Jimmy.
Yeah. Listen, I know you wanted me to go.
You have to do what's best for you.
Oof. Uh, I should go open up.
Um... sushi tonight?
Uh, yeah. Yeah, that sounds great.
Kim.
Hello, Rich.
- So good to see you.
- You too.
Thanks for seeing me
on such short notice.
Oh, are you kidding?
I've been wanting to thank you in person
ever since you sent
Billy Gatwood our way.
So, shall we?
So, how long you got with that thing?
- Three more weeks.
- Mm.
Can I sign it?
Do people still do that?
Please have a seat. Have a seat.
I won't lie.
Losing Billy Gatwood definitely hurt.
Well, if it makes you feel any better,
I think he misses you.
As long as he's taken care of, I'm happy.
Well, you made it easy for us.
We just continued what you started.
So, um, how is James holding up?
I didn't get to speak with him
at the funeral.
We're taking it one day at a time.
Mm.
Well, grief moves at its own pace.
And it's different for everybody, so...
Give him my best.
Thank you.
So, what can I do for you?
- I have a question for you.
- Mm-hmm.
How's your banking division?
Well, we have some banking work,
but I wouldn't say we have a division.
Would you like one?
Well, it's a good long way
from the rest of your operation.
It must remain completely separate.
Two bedrooms each.
Werner'll probably take his own,
and the rest of the guys can double up.
Wired and plumbed?
Yes.
Oh, this is a good start.
What do you have in mind?
Hmm.
Couple treadmills over there,
barbells, weight bench.
You build out a stocked bar, beer on tap.
I mean, they're German, so...
Entertainment system here, DVD player.
Projector and screen set-up
might be nice,
a few La-Z-Boys or couches, pool table.
I don't know. Foosball?
Hell, we could even put up a hoop.
Germans play basketball, yeah?
I believe so.
You know, Werner said that
this was gonna take 6 months,
which means 8 at least,
probably 10, in total isolation.
These guys are gonna be doing
10 hours heavy labor
every day... well, night.
Then coming home to this.
We can't just keep 'em alive.
We got to keep 'em
from climbing the walls.
Make a list.
Security.
I'd like a full camera perimeter inside,
and we'll keep it low-profile.
They'll know we'll be watching.
We just don't need
to stick it in their faces.
Outside, too, obviously,
in case someone tries
to find a way in or out.
I'll put a sally port on that door.
We'll control it from the outside.
And we're gonna need a trailer
to monitor the cameras.
Close by.
2 guys, 24-hour monitoring,
working shifts.
Let's say five guys, minimum.
Probably help to have a couple
German speakers, as well.
I can provide you men.
Well, I'm gonna need to vet 'em.
- No offense.
- Of course.
- What is it?
- Infection. Bad one.
I must leave.
Tell Tyrus what you need.
It will be done.
You got a pen?
- I'll remember.
- Yeah?
Treadmills.
You want to check wholesale providers.
These guys are gonna tear
right through consumer-grade.
I'd love to see what something,
say, like a 24-footer, would run me.
Uh, sorry.
We just don't make them that big.
Who does?
- I can't think of anyone around here.
- Yeah.
Well, who makes those huge signs
that the casinos have?
Um...
You know what? Never mind.
Thank you very much.
Jimmy McGill.
Uh, yes.
I'm looking for Jimmy McGill.
Yeah. You found him.
The lawyer?
Yeah. Wh... What can I do for you?
My name is Brett Dunst.
I think you did my aunt's will?
At least, that's what it says here.
She, um... She died.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- Thanks.
I'm the executor,
and I distributed all her stuff,
but there's some kind
of finer details in this thing
that are real tricky.
I thought maybe you could
help me with those.
Who was your aunt?
Geraldine Strauss.
Oh, Mrs. Strauss passed away?
H-How?
She, um... She went in her sleep
a couple weeks ago.
Heart failure.
Oh.
- Hello?
- Um...
Did Clarence get the Alpine Shepherd Boy?
I'm sorry?
Uh, the Hummel.
Oh, the little figure.
Yeah, yeah, he got it.
So, uh, he finished college then?
Yep. Just this last semester.
Well, good. That's... That's good.
How did you kno...
Oh, because you did the will. Right.
Is there a memorial?
Uh, sorry. It was last week.
Anyway, it's my busiest time at work,
and Angie's doing the best she can,
but I have to get back to Salt Lake.
Are you on an hourly rate,
or would this be, like,
a flat-fee kind of thing?
Mr. McGill?
I'm sorry. I, uh...
I'm not practicing any longer.
Aw, darn it.
I can refer you, though.
Um... Hamlin Hamlin McGill
has an excellent estate law department,
and they'll help you sort things out.
Just ask for Francis Scheff,
and he'll point you
in the right direction.
Hamlin Hamlin McGill.
McGill. Wait. Isn't that you?
Uh, it's just a coincidence.
All right. Well, thank you, Mr. McGill.
You bet.
God damn it.
My husband and I
scrimped and saved for so many years.
We did our best to build a nest egg
so that we wouldn't
be a burden to our family.
After Ronald passed, I moved
to an assisted-living facility,
a nice place.
They told me they'd take care
of everything,
but then one day, they said
all my money was gone.
How could that be?
Where did it all go?
If you or a loved one is a resident
of a Sandpiper Crossing facility...
...or other associated
retirement community,
you may be eligible to receive
compensation for...
Hey there.
Hey.
Guess where I am.
Somewhere good?
Somewhere very good.
You could be here, too.
Hey there.
Hey... Giselle.
I was thinking
we could just be Kim and Jimmy today.
Ah. Okay.
Those two aren't all bad.
Rumors and hearsay.
How's work?
It is a job.
And how about you? Work's good?
Yeah. Actually, I have news.
Good news.
It's great news, really.
It could change things for Wexler/McGill.
But I met with Rich Schweikart today.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Well, you know, they took on Gatwood,
so I've been meaning to follow up.
And ahh anyway, we were talking,
and he offered me a job.
Again?
What? He can't take no for an answer?
They want me to run
their banking division.
Build it, really.
You're not seriously considering it?
I'd be coming in as a partner.
But I thought things were going okay
with Mesa Verde since, uh...
They are. They were.
My workload has gotten
a lot more complicated lately.
I've been taking on some pro bono work,
overflow from
the public defender's office.
P.D. overflow? When did you... Why?
I like it.
I'm good at it.
And I'm helping people, Jimmy.
And I know that sounds cheesy.
It's, you know, it's whatever,
but it's the truth.
No. It, uh, makes a lot of sense.
I have been thinking about
criminal law myself lately
you know,
for when I get my license back.
Really?
Yeah.
You know, like you said,
you know, you're helping people.
I'm thinking an office
in one of these refurbished bungalows,
you know, downtown by the courts,
you know, stick around where all
the people who need help are.
Boy.
It has a nice ring to it now...
"Wexler/McGill... criminal law."
That all sounds great.
The thing is,
if I go to Schweikart and Cokely,
I have all those associates
to help cover Mesa Verde.
It'll keep paying the bills
and free me up to do
the work I really care about.
So, you kind of get to have
your cake and eat it, too.
Kind of, yeah.
I'll be right back.
- No. Jimmy.
- What?
I... No, I just... I got to hit the head.
I say do it.
It's a great opportunity,
and you should jump on it.
You mean that?
Yeah.
Kim, you got to do what's best for you.
You sure?
Yes.
I can't ask you to wait around for me.
And who knows?
10 months, a lot can happen.
Yeah.
Yeah. Who knows?
Yeah. So, um, to Schweikart and Cokely...
and Wexler.
Hi.
I only have a few minutes.
I have to pick Kaylee up.
Okay.
What did you want to tell me, Mike?
I stand by what I said.
The guy's a charlatan.
But there's a time and there's a place,
and that wasn't it.
You left me quite the mess.
Yeah. I can see that.
It'll be okay eventually.
Anita's not happy.
You might want to call her.
Probably better if I don't.
You know that I would never forget Matty.
I know.
No one expects you to wear a hair shirt
for the rest of your life.
Same goes for you.
You and Kaylee okay?
We're good.
Then I'm good.
I... was thinking
maybe I could pick Kaylee up
from school tomorrow.
Yeah, that'd be a big help, Pop.
See you then.
Okay.
No, no. I'd tell you.
Nobody's heard anything.
You can go in, Jimmy. He's expecting you.
- Thanks, Julie.
- Mm.
Oh, hey, Jimmy.
Howard.
This was going in the mail today.
You would have gotten it by Friday.
Yeah. I got a pressing need
only $5,000 will cure.
Well, there you go then.
Everything correct?
Looks good. Thanks.
Of course.
Hey, I, uh, see a lot
of empty cubicles out there.
What's going on?
We're doing some reorganizing.
Just making the office a little
more fêng shui, I take it?
We've had some setbacks.
Paying out to Chuck's estate?
That is part of it.
And to be frank,
the firm's reputation is...
not what it was.
So, what's the plan?
The consultants call it "rightsizing."
No. I mean what's the plan
to get HHM back on its feet?
Are you kidding me? I...
I just referred a client to you guys.
You're welcome, by the way.
And you're telling me
this place is falling apart?
Get your shit together, Howard.
- Excuse me?
- Oh, please.
You suffer one little setback,
and you're gonna let
your entire legacy go?
- One little setback?
- Fine.
Your pain is very special. Woe is you.
Just stop wallowing, okay?
This place is all you've got!
That and your hair, which, let's face it,
clock's ticking there, too, so...
You want to save your business?
You want to save your dignity?
You're gonna have to fight.
Hey.
You're a shitty lawyer, Howard.
But you're a great salesman.
So get out there and sell.
Fuck you, Jimmy.
There you go. Use that.
That's $4,000, please.
- Here's a tip.
- Thank you very much.
- Pleasure doing business with you.
- You, as well.
Sorry.
All set over here.
You got a spot yet?
Piñatas? Are you kidding?
No, no, that could... could work, yeah.
Regardless, we have full run
of the place?
There's no prying eyes?
All right.
Well, that's it, then.
Ah, she's fine.
Yeah, I change half the water
in the tank every week.
She's good.
No. I know. Don't over-feed.
I... All right, goodbye.
What are you doing?
Oh! Mrs. Nguyen.
Just, you know, step right on in
anytime, you know?
What's all this?
It's a side business.
I thought you were a lawyer.
I've had a temporary setback.
Lost your job again?
Did you need something, Mrs. Nguyen?
I don't want people coming in and out
to buy your stupid phones.
I'm not gonna sell them
out of the office,
so don't worry about it.
You can't keep them here.
Uh, I pay rent for this place,
so I can do whatever I want with it.
They're a fire hazard.
Well, they're not gonna
be here very long, okay?
Hmm.
That's... That's on me.
No, it's, uh, prepaid, 350 minutes.
Get-rich-quick schemes never work.
Just watch me!
The doctor tells me
your fever has gotten worse.
They say this infection may kill you.
Even if it doesn't...
my doctor tells me again and again
that you may never wake.
And yet I wait.
I grew up quite poor.
We lived in the hills,
in a place my brothers built
from things they found...
metal sheeting, plywood.
When it rained, it smelled like hay.
We were always hungry.
But there was a lucuma tree,
scrawny, barely alive.
My family had given up on it
years before.
Never bore fruit.
When I was 7, I became fixated on it.
I watered it, tended to it.
It took a long time,
but the buds grew into green fruit.
I was so proud.
I didn't tell anyone.
I plucked one and hid behind our shack.
I ate the whole thing.
I'd never tasted something so sweet.
It was like caramel.
At first, we ate the fruit ourselves,
and then I began taking it
to the village to sell.
One day, much of the fruit
was gone from my tree.
Piece were scattered
on the ground, half-eaten.
I thought it was probably a coati.
Have you ever seen one?
About the size of a large housecat.
Opportunists.
I built a snare using branches and wire.
It didn't take long
for the animal to set it off.
But the coati thrashed so hard,
it broke out of the snare...
broke its leg, as well.
I tried to grab it, but it slipped away.
It ran under the house.
I knew it would show itself
sooner or later.
So I waited... for hours, into the night.
When my brothers called for me...
I did not answer.
I didn't make a sound.
I was so still.
Finally, it came out.
It knew I was there, but it was hungry.
This time, I was ready.
I caught it.
It fought me.
But I was stronger.
The merciful thing
would have been to kill it.
I kept it.
It lived for quite some time.
I believe you will wake, Hector.
Wow.
_
Crazy.
Hallo!
_
All right, gentlemen, we have
a few things to go over here.
That means you, too.
Kai.
Over here, Kai.
_
We've got four bedrooms
between the two houses.
I leave it to you to figure out
the roommate situation.
I assume you're all friends,
and I don't really want to hear
about it if you aren't.
Working kitchen so you can cook
whatever you want.
The refrigerators, the cabinets
are stocked with the essentials.
There's a shopping list.
You write down whatever you need,
and we'll get it.
There is a phone in each house.
It goes directly to me or one of my guys.
Anything you need, call.
So, when do the girls get here?
Anything within reason.
Any more questions?
All right.
You've got some time to relax
and settle in.
Work starts tomorrow night.
Michael.
They are all good boys.
Once the work begins, they focus.
I see to it.
What you've done here is very impressive.
Thank you for that, Michael.
Right.
If you need anything
to make this go better, you let me know.
I will, certainly.
Hey, Mike.
Hey.
You keep an eye on this one.
I come in peace.
I'm just... just here to make a deal.
What kind of deal?
Look, fellas, we... we got off
on the wrong foot, okay?
I'm sure you saw me out here
selling my wares,
and you thought I was just some rube,
out looking to score a quick buck
and just begging to be rolled.
But, guys, I'm thinking long term.
I see a real need in this community
for safe, affordable, untraceable phones,
and I'm ready to fill it.
Wah-wah-wah.
All right.
All right, straight talk.
I need to be able to sell my phones
without worrying
about getting ripped off.
I'm proposing
if you let me sell my phones
without hassle, I cut you in,
say, 100 bucks every night that I'm out.
And that's money
for literally doing nothing.
Why wouldn't we just take all of it?
'Cause I'm talking
consistent, reliable profits, you know?
Sure, you can rip me off again,
take all that I've got,
but then I stop selling,
and you lose a valuable revenue stream.
Give me all you got now.
I'm trying to make money
for all of us here.
Just work with me.
Give.
If you could just expand
your thinking a little bit.
You talk too much.
All right, all right,
we got a man of action.
You should have taken the deal.
You're, like, the stupidest
person I've ever met.
Didn't know I had friends, did ya?
So, what's it gonna be... fast or slow?
It's gonna hurt like a bitch either way.
What was that? Was it... slow?
Let me...
Aah!
We're sorry, man, all right? We're sorry!
Yeah, you are, very much so.
Look, we'll leave you alone, okay?
We... We won't mess with you anymore.
Easy to say now, but what about tomorrow?
I-I-I... I'll swear, man.
I'll swear on anything you want me to.
Cross your heart and hope to die?
Yes. Yes, man.
You mean it?
Yes.
Yes!
Look, after this, you'll never
have to see us again.
- Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
- And you will spread the word
that I'm off limits?
Yes. Yes.
Yes. We'll tell everyone.
We'll say, "D-D-Don't mess
with the cellphone guy."
All right, we're done.
We're done!
I think they get it.
Seriously, guys.
We're... We're done.
Okay. We're good, all right?
That's enough.
I appreciate the enthusiasm,
but he got the message.
That's right! L-Listen to what he says.
Listen to what he says.
I got the message.
Uh, you know what?
If it's that important to you, go ahead.
No, no, no, no, no!
No! No, no, no, please!
No. No, please. Please.
No, no, no, no. No, no, no.
No, no, no, please! Please don't!
You get one warning, and that was it.