Previously on "Better Call Saul"...
- My father is a simple man.
- I don't trust him.
[GASPING]
GUS: Call 911.
- [SIREN WAILS]
- He took these.
[PILLS CLATTER]
This is the first time
I've done this for anyone.
I don't know what you do,
but Mr. Fring must think
you're quite good at it.
Ehrmantraut. Security consultant.
I don't think what happened
was an accident.
He was improving until
the thing with the insurance,
so I forced him out.
Well, Howard, I guess
that's your cross to bear.
[HEART MONITOR BEEPING]
[LIQUID DRIPPING]
[BUTTON CLICKS]
[BEEPING CONTINUES]
[AIR HISSING]
[BED CREAKS SOFTLY]
[BEEPING, HISSING CONTINUES]
[INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT OVER P.A.]
[TRUCK HORN BLARES IN DISTANCE]
[CART RATTLING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
...6 every touchdown.
- ORDERLY: Who keeps track of all that?
- [FLASHLIGHT BUTTON CLICKS]
It's all on the computer.
Computer does everything.
Every stat gets converted into points.
I don't know. Sounds
kind of dumb, to be honest.
- I just want to watch the game.
- [SCOFFS]
You're just afraid to lose 20 bucks.
You want to bet on the game, let's do it.
Why do we got to mess
with all this extra stuff?
Trust me. You end up...
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
[FLASHLIGHT BUTTON CLICKS]
[BEEPING, HISSING CONTINUES]
[VEHICLES PASSING IN DISTANCE]
DOCTOR: He's no longer in a
coma, but he's unresponsive.
His condition is stable.
They're managing his blood pressure.
But whether he will wake up
and understand
what's going on around him,
there's no way of knowing.
That's unacceptable.
Gustavo, he's getting
very good care here.
There's very little even
the best hospitals could do.
Now, might it be different
if he was in the care of
someplace like Johns Hopkins?
Perhaps.
Or... it could make no difference at all.
But in the end...
in the end...
I can think of no better
judgment on this man.
Isn't this what he deserves?
I decide what he deserves.
No one else.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
♪♪
[MACHINE WHIRRING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[WHIRRING CONTINUES]
JIMMY: There she is!
Want some fresh O.J.?
JIMMY: Mmm, good. Vitamin C.
It'll help you heal quicker.
I don't think it works like that.
Eh, it might. You don't know.
I'm good.
[SIGHS] Oh, I've also got leftover bacon
from my breakfast sandwich.
That's got definite healing powers.
Okay. That I believe.
- [LIQUID POURS]
- And I made coffee
with a little cinnamon in it for flavor.
Just trying something different.
[MUFFLED] You're up early.
Yeah.
Oh, did I wake you with the noise?
No. No, no, not at all.
[SIGHS] I totally did, didn't I?
No. I was... I was getting up...
I'm sorry. ...eventually.
I've got job interviews lined up.
I wanted to get an early jump.
I'm starting down south...
office-manager interview in Polvadera.
Then I'm working my way up north
to Algodones.
I got a lot of ground to cover.
Jimmy, you know,
you can take some time off.
Nobody's gonna ding you
for not having a steady job
right this minute.
[SIGHS] Why wait?
[BRIEFCASE HANDLE CLACKS]
I don't want unemployment
hanging over my head,
and we could use another paycheck.
And, uh [SMOOCHES] besides,
this is your office now.
I don't want to be a distraction.
- But you're not a distraction.
- That's right.
'Cause I'm gonna be out there
finding me a job.
- JIMMY: Wish me luck!
- Good luck.
Oh, Thai or Mexican?
Hmm?
I'm gonna pick up dinner on the way back.
Oh. Uh, either. Your choice.
And what a choice it shall be.
Yeah. Okay, Jimmy, wait.
Are you...
You're not going to that meeting?
Nah.
Uh, if there's anything important,
Howard knows how to find me.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[ENGINE RUMBLING]
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
[VEHICLE BEEPING IN DISTANCE]
[KEYS JANGLING]
[LOCK POPS]
[ELECTRICITY HUMS, KEYCHAIN CLACKS]
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
[VEHICLES PASSING]
[TOOLS CLACK SOFTLY]
Papa.
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
[TOOLS CLACK]
[VEHICLES CONTINUE PASSING]
[KEYS JANGLING]
[LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS]
[KEYS CLACK]
[BOX CREAKS, PAPER RUSTLES]
[VEHICLES CONTINUE PASSING]
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
_
[SIGHS]
[SMACKS LIPS SOFTLY]
MANUEL: Mijo.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[BRAKES SCREECH]
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[SIGHS]
[SNIFFS]
[SMACKS LIPS]
[KEYS CLACK]
[CAR DOOR CREAKS SOFTLY]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[VEHICLES PASSING]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYS ON STEREO]
[SIGHS]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[COPIERS WHIRRING, CLICKING]
You see there... that's Alma.
And on the left is Ollie,
Mr. Neff's aunt and uncle.
They started this company
almost 50 years ago.
- Whoa.
- Hmm.
- Look at that.
- Yeah.
And we think that other fellow
is Frank Corker,
one of the early repairmen.
Oh, they must have relied on him a lot.
That's a Thermo-Fax.
Needed a specially coated paper
to get an image off one of those babies.
Oh. You know your stuff.
Ah, I worked in a mail room,
so I talked to a lot
of repairmen... a lot.
- [CHUCKLES]
- They love talking shop.
Yes. They are a lonely bunch for sure.
Uh, this one was a real big
seller for Neff,
really put us on the map.
- That's the 6500 color copier.
- Yeah.
That's a war-horse.
I mean, did you ever see
the guts of this beast?
It takes 15 seconds to get a printout.
I worked with one back in Chicago.
That machine was almost too good.
Counterfeiters used it
to make phony $5 bills.
[SMACKS LIPS] What?
Yeah.
That's... That's not right.
- [SCOFFS]
- [CHUCKLES] No.
Oh, oh, lookit here.
You got a lot of hardware over here.
- Yes.
- Phew.
Mr. Neff loves sponsoring the kids.
Bowling. That's fun.
We had a pretty good run in the '90s,
but, uh, we don't find kids
much interested anymore.
Yeah. This generation is all
hackey sack and video games.
[CHUCKLING] Ain't that the truth.
[SMACKS LIPS]
Hummels.
Yes. Those were Alma's.
She loved collecting the little
things, God rest her soul.
- Yeah. I knew a lady... same way.
- Hmm.
Ah, touring the wall of crap, I see.
I need to drag that stuff
to the dumpster,
just haven't had a chance
to motivate myself.
Mr. Neff, this is James McGill.
Oh, just "Jimmy" is fine.
Jimmy, pleasure. Come on down.
Have a seat.
Guessing Henry filled you in
on what we're looking for.
Oh, he did, indeed... um,
office-to-office salesman,
willing to have multiple doors
slammed in my face,
with one mission...
upgrade, upgrade, upgrade
their old copiers
to your top-of-the-line new ones.
Well, you think you have the chops?
It's a lot harder than it sounds.
Well, I'd sure love a crack at it.
I've been told stubbornness
and persuasiveness
are two of my top qualities. [CHUCKLES]
I have to say, Jimmy does know
his way around a copier.
- No kidding.
- [CHUCKLES]
Well...
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
[CLOCK TICKING]
Says here you were a lawyer...
up until not that long ago.
What changed?
Well, you know why God made
snakes before he made lawyers?
He needed the practice.
[LAUGHTER]
"Needed the practice." Yeah.
Right?
And that's pretty much
the only lawyer joke I know
'cause all the others are true stories.
[LAUGHS]
Look, I know you're looking for
somebody with sales experience,
and I don't have any,
except... except being a lawyer.
Look, being a lawyer, my job was sales.
I was selling to judges.
I was selling to juries.
Sometimes I was selling to clients
to take the best deal
from a series of bad options,
but every hour of every day,
I was convincing, persuading.
I was selling.
I hear what you're saying.
You know, we have a lot
of high-ticket items
and a clientele primed to say "no."
Well, my spirit animal is a Gila monster.
Once I latch on, I don't let go.
[LAUGHS]
I like it. I like it.
Well, you make a lot
of excellent points, Jimmy.
I can see why Henry
wanted me to meet you.
Well, thank you for coming down.
Yeah, absolutely. Anytime.
Yeah. We're gonna put our heads together,
have a decision in, say,
about a week or so.
Great. We'll let you know then.
- Thank you very much.
- You bet.
Great.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYS ON STEREO]
[SIGHS]
[COPIERS WHIRRING, CLICKING]
♪♪
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
♪♪
Yes?
I'm sorry. Could I just have
another minute?
Uh, I'll be real quick.
Uh, yeah, sure, Jimmy.
Uh, what's on your mind?
Look, I know you were
gonna take some time
and consider your options,
but maybe we can settle this right now.
There's a thing that we all know
called opportunity cost.
The time you spend looking for someone
is time I could be out there
working for you.
And, sure, there are salesmen out there
with way more experience than me.
But what are the chances
one of them's gonna come
walking through that door
in the next week?
And is it worth the wait?
Maybe. Maybe.
But I can tell you this.
None of them will have the connection
to your machines that I do... none.
I worked in the mail room.
I know how important the copy machine is.
Deadlines, last-minute changes,
and I was in there.
I was clearing paper jams.
I was cleaning ink off gears and rollers,
trying to figure out where the
mystery streaks were coming from.
[CHUCKLES] I was down
on my hands and knees,
with my tie over my shoulder
and ink-stained hands
and a line of assistants out the door,
and they're all worried that
they're gonna lose their job
if they don't get their document
in the next five minutes.
I know... I know better
than anyone that the copier...
it's the beating heart of any business.
It goes down, it causes delays.
That is lost money.
That is frustrated employees.
That's a negative work environment.
That's a business on life support.
But you plug one of your new machines
into the system... whew!
That is a healthy, strong heartbeat.
Ca-chunk, ca-chunk, ca-chunk.
That is a healthy business.
That is a successful business!
And that's what we're selling.
[CLOCK TICKING]
Um, just... a minute.
[VEHICLE PASSES IN DISTANCE]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
I don't need to...
[ENGINE STARTS IN DISTANCE]
I mean, it's kind of exciting.
I mean, it was great, and I think the
passion that this gentleman has...
Can you imagine sending that guy out?
Yeah. Come on.
Jimmy, welcome to the team.
Really?
- Damn right!
- [CHUCKLES] Congrats.
We'll get you set up with Audrey in H.R.,
fill out your paperwork,
and hopefully you'll be all set
by the end of the day.
[CHUCKLES] So, just like that, huh?
Yep. Why wait when we could
get you rolling?
You were gonna take some time, though,
and, uh, consider your options,
but, uh...
I just come in and did
that little song and dance,
and I'm in?
[CHUCKLES] Yeah. Right. That's right.
[CHUCKLES]
W... Are you out of your mind?
[SCOFFS]
You don't know me.
I just came in off the street.
You guys are like a couple of cats.
I come in and wave a shiny object around,
you're like, "I want that!"
[CHUCKLES] No due diligence?
No background check?
No. Just hire the guy
that says them fancy words?
I could be a serial killer!
I could be a guy who pees
in your coffee pot!
- I could be both!
- [SLAPS THIGH]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
So, you're not taking the job?
No, I'm not taking the job.
Suckers.
[BRIEFCASE HANDLE CLACKS]
I feel sorry for you.
[BIRD SQUAWKING]
[ENGINE STARTS IN DISTANCE]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[VEHICLES PASSING]
[SIGHS]
[INHALES SHARPLY, SIGHS]
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
[DIALING]
[SNIFFS]
Hello. Um, I'm wondering...
are you still interviewing
for the sales associate position?
Great. I could be there in,
um, 20 minutes.
James McGill.
Ellen. Okay. Wonderful.
Well, thank you, Ellen.
Uh, I'll see you soon.
[ENGINE STARTS, EXHAUST POPS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[METAL SQUEAKING]
Pop-Pop! Look how high I can go!
- [CHUCKLES]
- Yeah, that's good.
You be careful.
MAN: Want to do a couple more?
[CELLPHONE VIBRATING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
- Yeah, let's do another one.
- All right.
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
Yeah?
This is he.
[METAL CREAKING]
Meet at what time?
Yeah. I can be there.
You let her know.
Yeah.
All right, baby, time to get you
back to your mama.
Five more minutes?
Oh, honey, come on.
- Please?
- [SIGHS]
Five minutes.
You're on the clock.
[CHUCKLING] Thank you.
[DOOR OPENS]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYS]
[SCOFFS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Good afternoon.
Yeah. Madrigal Electromotive?
Straight down the hall,
the Sandia Room on your left.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
♪♪
[DOOR CLOSES]
LYDIA: Oh, good. Take a seat.
[DOOR CLOSES IN DISTANCE]
[CHAIR SCRAPES]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[PEN SCRATCHING]
[SIGHS]
You didn't come all this way just for me.
I frequently travel
to conference with distributors.
Albuquerque's one of many stops.
Hmm.
Okay.
I'm just [SIGHS] looking
for an explanation.
You steal an employee's badge,
waltz through my warehouse,
interfere with operations,
and strong-arm my facility manager.
Why?
I'm on your books
as a security consultant.
If I show my face in your warehouse,
it makes for a better cover story.
Anyone ever asks if I was there, I was.
Plus, you had a few things
that needed correcting,
so consider it a bonus.
That's not the point.
This is meant to be a paper transaction.
You sit at home,
and we pay you... your own money.
Doing what you did the way you did it
raises the threat of exposure.
The way I see it, it lowers the threat.
Like I said,
now there's a face to the name
that cashes the check.
So... what's your plan then?
Madrigal has eight terminals
in the southwest.
One down, seven to go.
Uh-huh.
And if I asked you to reconsider...
I'd ask you to do the same.
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES IN DISTANCE]
[PAPER RUSTLES]
At the moment,
you have Gus Fring's respect.
I'd want to keep that if I were you.
[DOOR OPENS]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[HEART MONITOR BEEPING, AIR HISSING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[CLIPBOARD CLACKS]
[TELEPHONES RINGING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE]
[DOOR OPENS]
[CART ROLLING]
Hello. Hi.
Sorry to interrupt.
Dr. Diseth, this is Dr. Maureen Bruckner,
just arrived this morning.
Nice to meet you. Hello.
Dr. Bruckner.
Dr. Bruckner is visiting
from Johns Hopkins,
and we're asking her to take the lead
with some of the more
severe cases in the ward,
including Mr. Salamanca.
- Johns Hopkins?
- Yes.
A generous grant came through,
which allowed Dr. Bruckner
to lend us her expertise.
Only temporarily.
I'm not here to step on any toes.
[TELEPHONES RING]
Okay, I... Well, our staff
can help with the database
whenever you're ready to pull records,
but I'm available anytime
if you have any questions.
Thank you.
Again, I-I don't want to step on toes.
We can co-manage care, if you like. We...
No. No. Uh, he's all yours.
[CHUCKLES] Thank you.
Good luck.
[BEEPING, HISSING CONTINUES]
Okay, um, well,
I will let you get to it then.
Let us know if there's anything
you need, anything at all.
DR. BRUCKNER: Absolutely.
Thank you.
Are you the family?
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
- [INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
- [ELEVATOR DINGS]
When did they get here?
Mm.
Don't worry. We're still running things.
[DOOR OPENS]
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
Okay.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
[BEEPING, HISSING CONTINUE]
MAN: It's just down here, sir.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Don Hector...
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
[BEEPING, HISSING CONTINUE]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS IN DISTANCE]
[BEEPING, HISSING CONTINUES]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
WOMAN: Right. Okay. Perfect.
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
[PLASTIC CLATTERING]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[VEHICLE DEPARTING]
[VEHICLES PASSING]
[CELLPHONE VIBRATING]
Yes?
LYDIA: It's me. Can we meet?
- Now is not a good time.
- I'm in town.
I can easily meet wherever's convenient.
GUS: Assume this is a secure line.
[SIGHS]
I spoke with your... security contractor.
I explained the situation again,
but he's going to keep doing
what he's doing.
GUS: I understand.
But... what he's doing makes no sense.
Do his reasons matter?
They do if he's unreliable.
He is reliable.
So I'm just supposed to let him
keep stealing my employees' badges?
I don't know
where he's gonna turn up next,
what disruption he's going to cause,
what mess I'm gonna have to clean up.
This isn't something I want
to spend my time worrying about.
Then I suggest you give the man a badge.
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
[VEHICLES PASSING]
TYRUS: Varga and Salamanca's
man... Colón...
they came by in the afternoon.
Nephews were in his room all day.
Bruckner saw him three times,
couple of specialists with her.
They took him for a brain scan.
And?
That's everything. No change.
♪♪
[PAPER RUSTLES]
You want me back at the hospital?
♪♪
No.
Call Victor.
Have him meet us.
♪♪
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[METAL CLANKING]
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
[TONES PLAY]
[ELEVATOR DOORS OPEN, CLOSE]
[CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE]
Just a few more.
I know Chuck was thorough,
but even I didn't think
there was gonna be this much paperwork.
Having worked with him as long as I did,
I was actually pleasantly
surprised by his restraint.
This is the agreement
for the transfer of property,
- as discussed.
- Mm-hmm.
If you can initial here...
and right down here.
- Am I late?
- Kim. No. Right on time.
We were just finishing up
Rebecca's side of things.
Hi, Rebecca.
It's nice to see you again.
I'm sorry we didn't get a chance
to talk more at the service.
Oh, well, I don't think anyone
felt much like talking.
Jimmy's not coming.
I'm here on his behalf.
JULIE: And that should do it.
I apologize for bringing us together
so soon after Chuck's service.
Um, it's really my fault.
Howard's being polite.
Thank you, Julie.
In any event [SIGHS] we thought
since Rebecca was still in town,
better to talk
through the estate in person.
Sure.
Chuck left the house to Rebecca,
and, as executor, I'll be
liquidating the property.
Uh, Howard suggested...
and of course I agree...
that it would be the right thing
for Jimmy to go through whatever survived
and take whatever he wants...
I mean, anything with sentimental value.
HAMLIN: We can set up a time.
The estate can provide
a truck and storage
for anything he chooses to keep.
That's okay.
Jimmy doesn't want any of it.
You sure?
I-I think the garage is pretty intact,
uh, except for some water damage.
He doesn't want it. Thank you.
Okay. I understand.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Well, then, as far as Jimmy's concerned,
all that's left is for him
to sign this agreement letter.
Once that's done, we can disperse
his share of the estate.
Let me guess. $4,000?
$5,000.
It's what you give when you want
to cut someone out of a will
but not have it contested,
just enough money to show
the recipient wasn't forgotten.
Chuck also left a substantial endowment
for a scholarship for deserving youth.
I was hoping Jimmy would agree
to serve on the board.
I'll let him know.
What else?
Well... Chuck left Jimmy
a personal letter.
His eyes only.
Howard, thank you for everything
that you've done.
I know it's been difficult.
It's hard on all of us.
Well, I don't want to keep you.
Let me walk you out.
Actually, Howard, we have
a few more things to discuss.
Uh, Kim, please give Jimmy my best.
I will.
It was very nice seeing you, Rebecca.
You too.
Safe travels.
[SIGHS] Kim.
I just, uh...
I just... had to know.
What were you thinking?
About?
What were you thinking
when you came to Jimmy
on the day of his brother's funeral
and laid that shit on him?
That Chuck killed himself?
What's wrong with you?
I-I thought...
[CLEARS THROAT]
I thought I owed it to Jimmy to tell him.
Owed it to him?
Did you owe it to Rebecca?
You tell her your theory?
That Chuck intentionally
set himself on fire?
I guess not.
I guess you just saved
that one for Jimmy.
Kim, I didn't do it to hurt Jimmy.
No. You did it to make
yourself feel better.
That... That's not
- what I was trying to do.
- To make yourself feel better
by unloading your guilt.
Who cares what it does to Jimmy, right,
as long as Howard Hamlin is okay?
Kim, I-I don't think that's fair.
Fair?!
Let's talk about fair.
Hey, let's let Jimmy dig around
the fire-damaged wreck
where his brother died screaming!
And then let's let him pick up
a keepsake or two.
That is so, so fair!
And did I hear you right?
You want him to serve on the board
of a scholarship committee?
A scholarship that Chuck
never in a million years
would have given to Jimmy.
Never!
It is just... I mean...
Oh, what's this, too, huh, Howard?
What's in this?
One last, "Screw you, little
brother," from beyond the grave?
Am I really supposed to do this to him?!
[VOICE SHAKING] All right, Kim.
[NORMAL VOICE] What can I do
to make it better?
Nothing.
There is nothing you can do.
Just stay away.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[LOCK DISENGAGES, DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES] Hey.
- I hope you're hungry.
- I bought way too much food.
Uh, yeah, I can always eat.
JIMMY: Counter or couch?
Uh, couch is good.
Couch it is.
If I remember correctly,
in, uh, five minutes,
one of the classic-movie
channels is showing,
uh, "White Heat" without interruption.
The other is showing "Jaws 3"
with commercials,
so a real Sophie's choice.
It is "Jaws 3-D," to be exact.
Ah.
But Cagney wins this one.
All right.
Hey, I got us, uh, Thai iced teas,
unless you want me to pour you something
a little less non-alcoholic.
No. I'm good with that.
So, how was the job search?
Pretty good. I, uh, got a couple leads.
Actually, I got an offer.
- Really?
- Yeah.
But, uh, it didn't feel quite right.
It was, uh...
It just wasn't a perfect fit.
But I think I might get a call back
on one or two of the others.
Wow. This was a pretty good first day.
You know, somebody's
gonna be lucky to get you.
[EXHALES SHARPLY, CLICKS TONGUE]
And how was your day?
I just mostly stayed here.
Trying to get organized.
No pressure from Paige and Kevin,
but I got to get
back on the horse, right?
You are right.
And, uh, the movie's about to start.
So, where is the remote?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ON TV]
♪♪
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[VEHICLE PASSES]
♪♪
[BED CREAKS]
[SIGHS]
[KEYS CLACKING]
♪♪
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[BUTTON CLICKING]
♪♪
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[BUTTON CLICKS]
Phew.
♪♪
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[SIGHS]
[KEYPAD BEEPS, DIALING]
[SNIFFS, SIGHS]
[LINE RINGING]
MIKE: I'm not available at the moment.
- Leave a message.
- [LINE BEEPS]
[SNIFFS] Hey. It's me.
Listen, I got something for you.
It's a job.
I think you're really
gonna like this, so call me.
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[ENGINE REVS]
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
We're taking six tonight.
What?
Six keys. It's what the boss would want.
You gonna back me up or what?
Yeah.
[ARTURO BREATHES DEEPLY]
Where's the rest?
I only see five.
That was a one-time-only.
Not the way we see it.
That's the way it is.
Salamancas get six.
We're not leaving without six.
[ELECTRICITY HUMMING]
Your boss isn't giving orders.
He can barely even open his eyes.
I'm giving the orders.
Take the five or leave with nothing.
[HUMMING CONTINUES]
[GUN COCKS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS]
Do you want to go?
♪♪
You heard him.
Six.
Put it away.
♪♪
You really want to do this?
[BAG RUSTLES, ZIPPER OPENS]
♪♪
[GUN CLICKS]
Yeah. That's what I thought.
♪♪
[ZIPPER OPENS]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
♪♪
[BAG RUSTLES]
That's how you do it.
We had them pissing their pants.
♪♪
[GRUNTING]
[ZIP TIE CLICKS]
♪♪
[GASPING, GROANING]
[ZIP TIE CLICKS]
♪♪
[MUFFLED SHOUTING, GASPING]
- [GASPING]
- [BAG CRUNCHING]
♪♪
I know what you've done.
The Salamancas... they do not.
[ARTURO GASPING]
Do you understand what I'm saying?
♪♪
- [GASPING]
- [BAG CRUNCHING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Look at me.
[GASPING]
♪♪
From now on, you are mine.
- [GASPING]
- [BAG CRUNCHING]
♪♪
[GASPING STOPS]
[CRUNCHING STOPS]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[FOOTSTEPS DEPARTING]