Previously on "Better Call Saul"...
KIM: Drop me off at
the courthouse, would you?
The group has heard my story
over and over.
Well, that's what we're here for.
How was the job search?
It just wasn't a perfect fit.
- Did you get it?
- Shittin' gold.
MIKE: Madrigal has eight
terminals in the southwest.
One down, seven to go.
"I'm proud we share the name McGill."
Man could write a letter.
I know what you've done.
The Salamancas do not.
_
[PANTS]
[THE VENTURES'
"GRAZING IN THE GRASS" PLAYS]
♪
[WOOD BLOCK THUDS]
[WATER RUNNING]
♪
[MUSIC STOPS]
[CLOCK TICKING]
You wanted me to talk.
I talked.
[TICKING CONTINUES]
♪
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
[ANDY GONZALEZ Y SUS AMIGOS'
"EL CUCUY" PLAYING IN DISTANCE]
MAN ON RADIO: [SPEAKING SPANISH]
♪
[DOG BARKS]
[SPEAKS SPANISH, SNIFFS]
[VEHICLE PASSES]
♪
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING, LAUGHTER]
[HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING]
♪
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[WOMAN LAUGHS]
[ "EL CUCUY" CONTINUES]
[MID-TEMPO DANCE MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOG BARKING]
♪
[DOOR RATTLES]
["EL CUCUY" CONTINUES]
[METAL SCRAPES, PANEL CREAKS]
[HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[MAN RAPPING IN SPANISH]
[MONEY COUNTER CLICKING]
♪
[DOOR SLAMS, LOCK ENGAGES]
[ENGINE REVS IN DISTANCE]
[DOG BARKS]
[MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS IN DISTANCE]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
♪
[SIGHS]
- [CAR DOOR CLOSES]
Done.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[GEAR SHIFT CLICKS]
[WATER RUNNING]
[CELLPHONE VIBRATING]
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
James McGill.
MAN: James, hi.
It's Robbie Finn from CC Mobile.
Hi.
Am I calling at a bad time?
No. It's fine. Um...
Great. Well, good news...
if you're still interested,
we'd like to offer you
a position at our uptown branch.
Oh, this is the cellphone store?
You bet!
You made quite an impression on Mr. Boyd.
He's talking about starting
you off as a shift supervisor.
We can get your training done
today, if that works for you.
[WATER RUNNING CONTINUES]
James? You still there?
[INHALES SHARPLY]
I'm sorry.
Uh, my plans have changed.
I'm not gonna be able to take that job.
Yeah? I'm sorry to hear that.
Me too. It's a real shame.
Alright, well, have yourself
a good day, James.
You too.
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[CELLPHONE THUDS]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[VEHICLE PASSES]
[FAUCET RUNNING]
You taking off?
Yeah.
Hey, you want Thai for dinner?
I got a hankering for that iced tea.
Yeah. That sounds good.
I should be back by 7:00.
Excellent.
What's up?
I was thinking that...
[FAUCET SQUEAKS, SHUTS OFF]
...maybe you should talk to someone.
[WATER SLOSHES]
[EXHALES SHARPLY] Yeah?
Yeah. I got a name.
He's not far from here.
I've heard good things.
Thought you'd give him a call.
A shrink?
It works for a lot of people.
Yeah. Okay.
Um... [SMACKS LIPS]
Yeah, well, thank you.
Um... I just, uh, have to, uh...
[WATER SLOSHES, SPLASHES]
I hafta check out my schedule and...
[RAZOR SCRAPING] Oh, geez.
- [WATER SLOSHES]
- [CHUCKLES]
I almost forgot to tell you.
[SIGHS]
I got a job.
- Really?
- Yep.
You're looking at Albuquerque's newest
mobile communications specialist.
I'm a shift supervisor, even.
Be very impressed.
Cellphone sales.
I-I'm selling cellphones.
CC Mobile. I start today.
- Jimmy, that... that is great.
- Yeah.
It's strictly gainful employment,
and then 10 months from now...
poof! I'm a lawyer again.
All right.
But you'll just give him a call
when you get a chance?
Of course. Absolutely.
Okay. Coffee's on.
Have a good first day.
You can count on it!
- [CLEARS THROAT]
- [KEYS CLACK]
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CREAKS, CLOSES]
[DIALING]
[SIGHS]
Mr. Finn, James McGill.
Listen, I've been thinking
it over, and I just can't
pass up this opportunity...
if the position is still open?
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[BELT WHIRRING]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
[DOOR OPENS]
- Hey, Marty.
- Morning, Kim.
What's on for today?
Well, let's see.
Papadoumian has settlement
conferences most of the morning.
Judge Clark has a pair
of corporate bankruptcies.
Munsinger looks
like criminal trespassing,
aggravated stalking,
and some pleading down.
Okay. Thanks.
You got it.
And you'll have another 14 days
from when they file
to tell me if you want to amend
your request for a pre-trial conference
or keep it the way it is.
I-I gather you're planning to amend, yes?
- MAN: Yes, Your Honor.
- Fine.
We'll reconvene in 30 days
for a proper pre-trial
conference, shall we?
I'll have an order out tomorrow.
[FOLDER THUDS]
Okay. Next.
WOMAN: CR2003114576,
State vs. Scotty Blakey.
Uh, Ms. Wexler,
do you have a matter
before the court today?
No, Your Honor. Just observing.
- All right.
- [DOOR CLOSES]
Uh, counsel?
Good morning, Your Honor.
Crystal Eitzmann on behalf of the State.
It's your turn.
- [LIGHT LAUGHTER]
- Oh, okay.
I'm Scotty Blakey, here for myself.
Mr. Blakey, you're here right now
because I called this case last
week and you didn't show up...
hence, the bench warrant.
- Understood?
- Yes.
Your Honor, Mr. Blakey was given
a six-month suspended sentence,
along with the one-year provision.
There's no question
that this bench warrant
constitutes a clear violation
of a very generous deal.
I'm doing the community service.
- The deadline already passed.
- Judge Munsinger would like
to see you in chambers
at the next recess.
EITZMANN: Why do you think you
were summoned in the first place?
The State was prepared
to charge this case as a felony
and agreed to drop it to a misdemeanor
in order to avoid wasting
the court's time and resources.
It's a sha...
MUNSINGER: In!
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Oh, I don't want to bother you
while you're eating.
Sit! Help me take my mind off this.
Eggplant and okra.
My wife insists.
Cholesterol, yadda yadda.
[CHUCKLES]
[CLEARS THROAT]
[CHEWING LOUDLY]
Hurt your arm, huh?
Yes.
Are you researching something?
No, Your Honor.
Then you're... you're working
on your procedure.
Just... observing.
Mm.
Oh, so, Howard Hamlin's fine
with one of his associates
just sitting around my court all day,
whiling away the billable hours?
Actually, I left HHM.
- I'm a solo practitioner now.
- No kidding.
Field?
Mainly banking.
How's business?
Pretty good.
I'm outside counsel for Mesa Verde.
Mesa Verde.
[SMACKS LIPS]
You know, I... I heard about a case,
and I think you might
be the right person for it.
Interested?
Uh, of course.
I can't share all the details just yet,
but I can give ya broad strokes.
There's a young woman, early 20s,
pregnant with her first child,
nearing the end of term.
Healthy as a horse.
She develops a complication.
She goes to the hospital for delivery,
and there's a mistake
with the anesthesia.
She aspirates vomitus
into her oxygen mask,
stops breathing.
The baby's delivered... fine.
But the young mother suffers
serious brain damage.
She's left comatose on a respirator.
The family is naturally devastated.
And they're broke,
so they have no way to pay
for the young lady's care.
And to make matters worse,
the hospital refuses
to take responsibility.
And they've hired
one of the most expensive
firms in the state.
This is the plot of "The Verdict."
Yes! Of course it is!
Because movies are the only place
where those
once-in-a-lifetime cases exist.
You know what I got coming up next?
I got a janitor who threw
his pee on his boss.
The one after that,
she stabbed her boyfriend
over a grilled cheese sandwich.
This is the real world,
Ms. Wexler, and you won't find
any save-the-broken-lawyer cases in it.
Don't think that you are the first
to try to rediscover their love
of the law by trolling my court.
You're not.
Best thing you can do
is stick to Mesa Verde.
Make lots of money.
Give some to charity.
[SMACKS LIPS]
And having said, that we've got
perpetual PD overload.
So beware.
Next time I see you lurking in my court,
I'm gonna put you to work.
Understood.
Good luck to you.
[CHEWING LOUDLY]
Thank you... Your Honor.
[BRIEFCASE CLACKS]
BAILIFF: All rise.
[GRUNTS]
Uh, good afternoon. Please be seated.
Case CR2003114882,
State vs. Lester Downes.
You wanted to discuss
the conflict of interest.
Yeah, before we get started, I'll, uh...
I'll address the defense's motion
to disqualify opposing counsel.
Well, I read your brief
very carefully, but I'm not...
[JIMMY LIDELL'S "IMMUNE TO LOVE"
PLAYS ON STEREO]
♪ You always seem to pass love by ♪
[CASH REGISTER RATTLES]
♪
[BELL DINGS]
MAN: Order's up.
[SILVERWARE CLINKING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
♪ She's immune to love ♪
♪ I'm sure of that now ♪
♪
- Sorry I'm late.
- Hey.
♪ She's immune to love ♪
♪ We can't see how ♪
- Paper?
- Thank you.
♪ You seem to hate more ♪
22 across is "Esmeralda."
♪
"Bill ringer's love interest."
It's the Hunchback.
Oh, Quasimodo. Look at you.
[CHUCKLES]
- Hey, Anita.
- Hey, Fran.
Usual for you?
- [LIQUID POURS]
- Yep. Thanks.
Yeah. Thank you, Fran.
You're welcome.
♪
You know, a girlfriend of mine
is playing piano with her band
tonight at The Launchpad.
They're pretty good. You wanna go?
Tonight's group.
Mm, we could ditch.
I'd better go.
I told Stacey I'd be there.
Sure.
[CUP THUDS]
Maybe I could stop by after.
That'd be great.
♪
You know, speaking of group,
I've been thinking
about reaching out to Henry.
I think he needs a friend.
Every time I see him, he seems worse.
Henry's fine.
- You talked to him?
- Don't need to.
Then how do you know?
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Because that dead wife
he's always talking about
never existed.
♪
[SCOFFS] What are you talking about?
It's an act.
Why would you even say that?
The guy's story changes
every time he tells it.
Really?
No, I don't think so.
That romantic night at the
Cubs game, their first kiss?
- Yeah?
- Never happened.
You can't know that.
Wrigley Field didn't get lights
until '88.
There were no night games before then.
None of his details add up.
Well, maybe he just got the year wrong.
♪
Why would anyone
make up a story like that?
FRAN: Okay.
Here you go.
FRAN: Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Thanks, Fran.
♪
You know...
[SMACKS LIPS] you have
a very suspicious nature.
Hmm.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Watch him.
He's got a tell.
Like a bad poker player, when he's lying,
he rubs his wrist.
Okay.
You want to put your money
where your mouth is?
Well, you gonna come to group tonight?
Make it interesting.
♪
All right.
10 bucks says that when he talks
about Judy, different story.
All right. You're on.
- All right.
- [CHUCKLES]
[VEHICLES PASSING]
[UP-TEMPO INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC
PLAYS ON STEREO]
[VEHICLES PASSING]
♪
[SOFT ROCK MUSIC PLAYS ON STEREO]
[MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ON STEREO]
♪
[SOFT ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[HORN HONKS, VEHICLE PASSES]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
♪
CC Mobile. This is Jimmy.
FINN: Hey-o. How was the first morning?
Good, Robbie.
Um... well ya, actually,
it's a little... little slow.
Yeah, that store's always
been a bit calmer.
Just bring a book.
So, this is a normal weekday?
Mostly, but wait till inventory week.
There's a line out the door.
When's inventory week?
Uh, you just missed it.
Is there, uh, any chance
that you could move me
to a store with a little more traffic?
Uh, let's see.
The Gold Street store is always hoppin'.
Uh, but it looks like the
schedule's all full right now.
Let's give it a couple weeks,
and then we'll see.
Uh, no problem.
If I can, I'll swing by later.
Keep up the good work.
Yeah. See you then. Bye.
[PHONE HANGS UP]
♪
[BALL BOUNCES]
[BALL BOUNCING]
♪
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
[MAN SPEAKING SPANISH]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[INHALES SHARPLY] Hmm.
[ENGINE RUMBLES]
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
NACHO: [SPEAKING SPANISH] _
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
_
[DOORS OPEN]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Hey, amigos.
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
[FOOTSTEPS DEPARTING]
[NACHO BREATHING SHAKILY]
[SHOUTING IN SPANISH]
- Aah!
- Ugh!
[BODY THUDS]
- [CRICKETS CHIRPING]
- [NACHO BREATHES DEEPLY]
[DOG BARKING]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[VEHICLE PASSES]
[GUNSHOTS]
[RAPID GUNFIRE, INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
Salamancas.
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES, GLASS SHATTERS]
[MAN SCREAMS]
♪
[GLASS SHATTERS, DOG BARKS]
[GUNFIRE AND SHOUTING CONTINUE]
♪
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
[GLASS BREAKING, VEHICLE APPROACHES]
[TIRES SQUEAL]
♪
[TIRES SCREECH]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
[NACHO BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
♪
[PANTING]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
♪
[GUN COCKS]
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
♪
[GUNSHOTS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
[GUN CLICKS]
♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
[EXPLOSION]
[RAPID GUNFIRE, GLASS SHATTERING]
♪
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
♪
[GUNFIRE]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BULLETS RICOCHETING]
[SHELL CASINGS CLATTER]
♪
[MAN SHOUTING IN SPANISH]
DEWEY: [SPEAKING SPANISH] _
_
♪
[GUNFIRE]
Ugh!
[SHELL CASINGS CLATTER]
- [GUN CLICKS]
- [MAN SHOUTS]
♪
[GUNSHOTS]
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
♪
[GUNSHOTS CONTINUE]
[BULLETS RICOCHET, CASINGS CLATTER]
[GROANING]
[GUNSHOTS CONTINUE]
♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
[SHELL CASINGS CLATTER]
♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
♪
[SIREN WAILS IN DISTANCE]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[GROANS SOFTLY]
[SIGHS]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[ENGINE RUMBLING]
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
[CAR DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
[GROANS SOFTLY]
[METAL RATTLING SOFTLY]
NACHO: We cleared out the Espinosas.
They're all done.
And the Salamanca brothers?
Marco took a hit, but he'll pull through.
They went back south
until the heat dies down.
It's territory, isn't it?
Salamancas wipe out the Espinosas.
Espinosa territory is up for grabs.
[EXHALES SHARPLY] The cartel
can't give it to the Salamancas,
so... I think they give it to you.
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING, WIND WHISTLING]
Get some rest.
You have more to do.
WILLA: It's a service to the people.
It really is. It's a nonprofit.
And it's a perfect fit, I mean,
what with his degree
in sociology and all.
I think he's really come a long way.
It... He hasn't even talked
- about getting a job until this week.
- [DOOR OPENS]
- The place is called the...
- [DOOR CLOSES]
MAN: Whoops. [CHUCKLES]
Sorry. Sorry.
MAN: Willa, you hadn't quite finished.
WILLA: It's called
the North Fourth Art Center.
I hope he takes the job.
Well, thank you, Willa.
That all sounds really promising.
Anyone else?
[CLOCK TICKING]
Stacey.
STACEY: Um... today,
I-I got up, and I took a shower.
Kaylee woke up on her own
and got herself ready for school.
It was just a regular morning.
I made French toast for breakfast,
and we talked about
the self-pasting toothbrush
she's making for the science fair.
I took her to school and went to work.
And then I realized it.
I don't know why
I noticed it just then, but...
I hadn't thought about Matty
all morning...
not once.
When I was making French toast,
why didn't I remember
that I-it's his favorite?
I think about Matty every single
time I make breakfast,
but not today.
And they weren't just minutes.
There were hours
that I didn't think about him.
And if I can go hours, then...
then... then why not a whole day?
Why not a whole week?
[VOICE BREAKING] I mean, what if
I lose the sound of his voice?
What if I forget him completely?
I mean, I know I won't.
That's, like, impossible, but...
[SNIFFLES]
I don't know. I'm just... I don't know.
Thank you, Stacey.
You're not alone, truly.
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
- And it might be painful,
but if... if you ask me,
I'd say it's progress.
I mean... a lot of us in this room
have felt the same things
you're talking about.
[CLOCK TICKING]
I know I have.
I keep trying to get there,
you know, to live in the here and now.
I know that's what Judy would
have wanted, but it's... hard.
This guy at work... I've been
avoiding him for the last two weeks,
ever since he got back from his
vacation to Australia.
[INHALES DEEPLY, SIGHS]
She always wanted to go to Sydney,
but money was tight.
Finally, we were gonna go, for our 25th,
and that's when she got her test results.
Ugh, God.
Mike, you have something you want to add?
You don't want to hear
what I have to say.
Well, we're ready if you are.
Yeah?
This guy was never married.
What are you talking about?
Mike, now, you know the rules.
Yeah, I know your rules.
He's been coming in here for months
selling you a bill of goods,
getting you all misty-eyed
and loving every minute of it.
- Pop...
- Stop.
That's just not true.
Yeah? Okay.
So, I'll go to the public library
and I'll get the papers from 1997
and I'll run a search on Judy DeVore,
beloved wife of Henry DeVore.
Tell me I'll find her obituary.
- [INHALES SHARPLY]
- She wanted to go to Australia?
Well, last month, it was Cuba.
Come on, Henry.
Let's look at the papers,
see if the math works.
Come on. Mike.
[CLOCK TICKING]
She's not there, is she?
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Go on. Say it.
You have no shame.
[CHAIR CREAKS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR SLAMS]
Well...
he came to the right place, didn't he?
He knew you wouldn't notice.
And you didn't.
All wrapped up in your sad,
little stories,
feeding off each other's misery.
[TICKING CONTINUES]
You wanted me to talk.
I talked.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[DOG BARKING]
[GEAR SHIFT CLICKS, ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
[VEHICLE DOOR OPENS]
[VEHICLE DOOR CLOSES]
[KEYS JANGLING]
[BARKING CONTINUES]
[DOOR CREAKS]
MANUEL: [SPEAKING SPANISH] _
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
[FLOORBOARDS CREAK SOFTLY]
_
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
[LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
Mijo.
NACHO: [SOFTLY] Papa.
[SIGHS]
Papa, no.
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
- [DIALING]
- [SIGHS] Papa.
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
_
DISPATCHER: 911. What's your emergency?
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
- Hello?
- [SPEAKING SPANISH]
911. What's your emergency?
[PHONE HANGS UP]
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
_
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
This one?
Unh-unh.
[VEHICLE BEEPING]
[METAL SQUEAKING]
How about this one?
No.
[ENGINE RUMBLING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE]
[AIR HISSES, MACHINERY WHIRS]
This one.
[SIGHS] Sure thing.
Hernandez and Sullivan.
They led the pack and load.
- [SCANNER BEEPING]
- My top guys.
Mhm-kay.
[METAL CLANKS]
[HORN HONKS]
[MACHINERY WHIRRING, CELLPHONE VIBRATING]
[VIBRATING CONTINUES]
[WHIRRING CONTINUES]
[WHIRRING, VIBRATING STOP]
[FLASHLIGHT CLICKS]
[METAL CLANGS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS IN DISTANCE]
[MACHINE BEEPING IN DISTANCE]
What's that say?
MAN: Uh...
It's not a guessing game.
38 degrees.
Should be 35.
Musta come in set wrong.
Goes out set right.
[HORN HONKS IN DISTANCE]
[CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE]
[MACHINERY WHIRRING]
Manifest doesn't say anything about...
Yeah. We'll fix that.
[CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE]
[METAL CREAKS IN DISTANCE]
[VEHICLE BEEPING IN DISTANCE]
These okay with you?
Are you talking about the strap?
I am.
Might be a little frayed,
but the rest of them are fine.
And you know this how?
[SIGHS]
So, we're pulling all the E track straps?
Is that a question?
[P.A. SYSTEM CHIMES]
We'll pull them.
MAN ON P.A. SYSTEM: Call for Ehrmantraut.
[HORNS HONKING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Ehrmantraut.
VICTOR: He wants to see you.
Yeah?
Tonight.
[RECEIVER SLAMS]
[DRILL WHIRS]
Hold on. We're not done yet.
[BALL THUDDING]
[SOFT ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
♪
[GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
♪
[VEST THUDS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[BRAKES SCREECH]
[ENGINE REVS]
[METAL THUNKING]
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[BRAKES SCREECH]
[GEARSHIFT CLICKS, ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[CANS THUDDING]
[BUZZER]
I'm a Fanta guy myself.
Yeah, well,
you can buy a truckload.
[GRUNTS]
Here you go.
[RUBBER BAND SNAPPING]
[PAPER RUSTLING]
[SNIFFS]
[MACHINERY WHIRRING, CLANKING]
[THUD]
Hey, whoa. Whoa. This is, uh,
more than we talked about.
Yeah, Bavarian Boy made quite a splash
at the collectibles expo.
Bidding war.
Wow. But great.
We both know you could have
kept most of this.
I-I would have never known
the difference.
Yeah, well, you could have
left me high and dry.
I'm liking this Hummel thing.
The cash came fast and clean.
Got any more where that came from?
Mm. No, not really.
Ah, bummer.
[DOLLY RATTLING]
We're gonna do this again.
I'll find something.
Sounds good.
When you do, call the vet.
Yeah?
Yeah. New job
[EXHALES SHARPLY] new phone.
You never know who's listening.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[ENGINE REVS]
[CARL RUTHERFORD'S
"TURN OFF THE FEAR" PLAYS]
♪ You've got to turn off the fear ♪
♪ When you've come down into here ♪
♪ While you're down here a-loadin' ♪
♪ The coal for the man ♪
♪ No, now, you can't be worried ♪
♪ 'Bout things that can go wrong ♪
♪ You gotta keep loadin' coal ♪
♪ And just ploddin' along ♪
♪
[MARKER SQUEAKS]
♪ You gotta pray that your
dear Lord is holding you near ♪
♪ And you turn off the fear
when you come into here ♪
♪ Yeah, turn off the fear
♪
[ENGINE RUMBLING]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[GRAVEL CRUNCHING]
[FENCE CREAKING]
[GATE CLOSES]
[VEHICLE DOOR CLOSES]
[GEARSHIFT CLICKS]
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[VEHICLE DOOR OPENS]
[VEHICLE DOOR CLOSES]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
You want to see me. Here I am.
In order for our arrangement to continue,
there is a matter we need to discuss.
Okay.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
Do you have something to tell me?
If you do, you would
be well advised to do so.
[SCOFFS]
Nacho Varga.
I wondered when you were
gonna get around to this.
You came to me.
You asked for a favor.
You looked me in the eye,
you shook my hand,
and all the while, you knew
Varga was moving against my interests.
I said I wouldn't kill Salamanca.
I never promised to be his bodyguard.
So... what now?
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
You gonna make a move,
you better make it.
But they're not gonna, are they?
You brought me here
because you have an ask.
So, why don't you stop
running a game on me
and just tell me about the job?