Previously on "Better Call Saul"...
You will appeal. We'll find a
way to make you look sincere.
Kim, I was sincere!
- You don't believe me.
- I drop everything for you!
You want to know why the
committee called you insincere?
Because you didn't mention Chuck.
NACHO: He's got a chicken
farm way out of town.
Show me.
You want to see your wife?
More than anything.
Then finish the job.
Get the lights.
KIM: You still want to be a lawyer?
- JIMMY: Yeah.
- Well, we can start with that.
KENNETH: My name is Kenneth Kazanjian,
partner with the firm Reeves & Green.
I'm here before you today
to vouch for Daniel Stark.
Your Honors, my name is Joseph Adamson,
Adamson, Field, and Wright.
It's my pleasure to stand
before you this afternoon
and vouch for Gina Robles.
Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm Charles McGill,
senior partner at
Hamlin, Hamlin, McGill.
I stand before you to
vouch for my brother,
James Morgan McGill.
Your Honors, Nathaniel
Scott, solo proprietor,
and I have the pleasure
to stand and vouch today
for Frances Yu.
[BONNIE TYLER' "TOTAL ECLIPSE
OF THE HEART" PLAYING]
♪ Forever's gonna start tonight ♪
♪ Once upon a time I
was falling in love ♪
♪ But now I'm only falling apart ♪
- Yeah, Ernie!
- Ernie!
WOMAN: Whoo!
ERNIE: ♪ Nothing I can do ♪
♪ A total eclipse of the heart ♪
- That one.
- Hmm?
- There. This one.
- No. I'm not doing that.
- Pick something else.
- Yes, you are singing that with me.
I'm not doing "Bohemian Rhapsody."
Besides, you're doing your
own song after Ernie.
I'm gonna do one by myself.
No.
- This is my night.
- Yeah.
I'm a lawyer now, all right?
I've been barred for
a whole three hours.
You know, you don't sing that with me
[SNAPS FINGERS] I sue you.
Okay, well, I'll just
sue you right back.
- Then I double-sue you.
- That is not a thing.
Well, it could be, you know,
once my full powers are unleashed.
You want to risk that?
♪ Turn around, bright eyes ♪
♪ Every now and then, I fall apart ♪
Oh, man, Ernie's really going for it.
- Yes. Yes, he is.
- Yep.
- ♪ Every now and then, I fall apart ♪
- [CHUCKLES]
- ♪ And I need you now tonight ♪
- Oh. [EXHALES SHARPLY]
Chuck's gonna bail.
- ♪ And I need you more than ever ♪
- Well, you know,
it's not really his kind of place.
Yeah, but, like, the
guy never has any fun.
I was hoping tonight he might,
you know, mingle with the lady folk.
Oh, he will, when he's ready.
♪ Together we can take it
to the end of the line ♪
♪ Your love is like a shadow ♪
- ♪ On me all of the time ♪
- I-I'm going in.
- Okay. Good luck.
- JIMMY: Pick a good one.
Not from this decade.
- ERNIE: ♪ I really need you tonight ♪
- JIMMY: Chuck.
Hey. Hey, buddy, you're not
leaving already, are you?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Jimmy, it's been great fun.
Really, it has.
But I've got early meetings.
- Come on. 10 minutes.
- [SIGHS]
- Just 10 more minutes. 10.
- Jimmy...
- You can do that.
- Jimmy.
You cannot leave. I'm up next.
- Oh.
- Yeah. Me.
If you leave now, tomorrow
you're gonna go to work,
and people are gonna tell you
how great my performance was.
You're never gonna forgive
yourself for missing it.
- [CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
- All right. All right, Jimmy,
- I'll stay for a little while longer.
- Great.
You... you won't regret it.
Now, come on. This is me.
[ABBA'S "THE WINNER
TAKES IT ALL" PLAYING]
[APPLAUSE]
[CHUCKLING] Okay.
[OFF-KEY] ♪ I don't want to talk ♪
♪ About things we've gone through ♪
♪ Though it's hurting me ♪
♪ Now it's history ♪
Get up here.
No.
♪ I've played all my cards ♪
♪ And that's what you've done, too ♪
Chuck McGill, everyone!
- Let's hear it!
- [APPLAUSE]
♪ Nothing more to say ♪
♪ No more ace to play ♪
♪ The winner takes it all ♪
That's you!
- ♪ The loser standing small ♪
- Yes! Let's go! Let's go!
No!
♪ Beside the victory ♪
- Yeah!
- Up there! Yeah!
♪ That's her destiny ♪
Whoo!
[LAUGHTER]
♪ I was in your arms ♪
- Okay.
- Yeah.
♪ Thinking I belonged there ♪
♪ I figured it made sense ♪
♪ Building me a fence ♪
♪ Building me a home ♪
♪ Thinking I'd be strong there ♪
♪ But I was a fool ♪
♪ Playing by the rules ♪
- ♪ The... ♪
- ♪ The gods may throw the dice ♪
- [CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
- ♪ Their minds as cold as ice ♪
♪ And someone way down here ♪
♪ Loses someone dear ♪
♪ The winner takes it all ♪
Okay.
Now, watch. Oh, watch your step, Jimmy.
All the way. That's it.
- That's it.
- [SLURRING] McGill and McGill,
- the brothers McGill.
- Yeah. Yeah.
[DOOR CLOSES]
- I'm a lawyer.
- Yeah.
- And you're lawyer.
- Yep.
- JIMMY: Two lawyers. How 'bout that?
- CHUCK: How 'bout that?
M&M.
Melts in your mouth, not in your hands.
- [CHUCKLING] Yeah.
- [CHUCKLES]
- All right.
- [KEYS JANGLE, THUD]
Hey, you got to tell Howard, uh,
to add another "M" to the firm
- 'cause it'll make it more symmetrical.
- Uh-huh.
And people love symmetricality.
- I can't argue with that.
- Yeah.
Oh, no, no. Come on, J... Sit...
Yeah.
- Okay.
- That'll do.
Okay.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
Yep.
- That's why God gave us two eyes...
- Oh?
You know, more pleasant to look at.
Hands and two feet,
thumbs and nipples.
We could get by with one nipple.
- Yeah.
- Am I right?
- [WATER RUNNING]
- You may be more right about this
than anything you've ever
spoken about before.
Thank you, Chuck.
Four or six nipples... it's interesting,
but I submit to the court it's, uh...
it's overkill.
H-H-M-M.
[CHUCKLING] "Hmmmmmm."
See? That's better.
H-H-M is just "Hmph." [CHUCKLES]
- No?
- Yeah.
You're writing this down.
Jimmy, I-I put a trash can by the bed
just in case, you know,
- in the eventuality...
- You think of everything.
You're very smart, Chuck.
All right. And there's some
water here for you, too.
Thank you.
[SIGHS]
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
CHUCK: What do you feel
like in the morning...
- eggs or pancakes?
- Pancakes.
JIMMY: Make those pancakes you make.
- Pancakes it is.
- Yeah.
[SNIFFS]
Get some rest, Jimmy.
You've had a big day.
JIMMY: Yeah.
A big day.
[GROANS] Yep.
- Good night, Chuck.
- Good night.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[OFF-KEY] ♪ The winner takes it all ♪
♪ The loser has to fall ♪
♪ Besi... ♪
- ♪ Beside the victory ♪
- ♪ Victory ♪
- ♪ That's her destin... ♪
- ♪ That's her destiny ♪
♪ I was in your arms ♪
♪ Thinking I belonged there ♪
- ♪ I figured it ♪
- ♪ It was... ♪
- ♪ It made sense ♪
- ♪ Sense ♪
♪ Building me a fence ♪
♪ Building me a home ♪
♪ Thinking I'd be strong there ♪
♪ But I was a fool ♪
♪ Playing by the rules ♪
[SIGHS]
♪ ♪
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
♪ ♪
MIKE: He's got a
three-and-a-half-hour jump on us,
but he started out on foot,
which gives us a fighting chance.
He doesn't have his passport,
so he's probably not
headed to the airport.
Doesn't know his way around town,
but if he gets to a bus or a taxi,
that's not gonna matter much.
Most likely ran off towards the highway.
You two, head north and south,
see if he's got his thumb out.
You two, go to the
train and bus stations
and use the cover story.
You, you stay with the crew,
- you keep them on lockdown.
- ANDRE: You got it.
[CAR DOORS CLOSE, ENGINES STARTING]
♪ ♪
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[PHONE KEYPAD BEEPING]
Yeah, um, I need the
number for Travel Wire.
Just connect me.
♪ ♪
Hi. I was, uh, wondering
if you could help me.
I arranged for my wife to wire me money
from Frankfurt, Germany, to the U.S.
- [CAR DOOR OPENS]
- The problem is,
she didn't tell me which branch.
Margarethe Ziegler.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
Yeah.
A-Albuquerque branch on Fourth.
I should have known.
Yeah. Thanks.
[TIRES SCREECH]
♪ ♪
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
JIMMY: Watermelon, pickles.
Watermelon, pickles.
One-thousand-one, one-thousand-two,
one-thousand-three.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
Oh. Hi.
It's very nice of you to come.
KEN: Of course.
You are Chuck's brother?
That's right.
- I'm Jimmy.
- Ken. Greenfield.
This is Emily Reed.
Hello.
We knew Chuck back in our time
with the Native Peoples
Education Council.
Oh, yes. I remember.
He spoke of you both quite fondly.
That means a lot.
I feel bad we lost touch for so long.
Well, you're here today, so...
We saw the notice about
- the law library dedication this weekend.
- Mm.
And today was the anniversary of...
I can't believe it's been a year.
It still doesn't make any sense.
[SIGHS]
Well...
So nice to meet you.
- God bless.
- Bless you.
Very thoughtful.
[GASPING]
Boo-hoo-hoo.
Boo-hoo.
[GASPS]
- KIM: Hey.
- Hey.
- You need some water?
- Coffee. [FINGERS SNAP]
And give me one of these bear claws,
please. All right.
You better pace yourself, though.
It's gonna be a long day.
Yeah.
But, hey, we got customers already.
That's a good sign.
I was afraid no one would show up.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
How'd it look?
How'd it feel?
Felt like I looked sad.
What's the headstone like?
Oh, Howard picked the big one.
But it's tasteful.
[SLURPS]
LALO: ♪ Hermoso cariño ♪
♪ Hermoso cariño ♪
♪ Estoy como un niño ♪
♪ Con nuevo jugete ♪
♪ Contento y feliz ♪
[HUMMING "HERMOSO CARIÑO" ]
[GRUNTS]
FRED: All right, just sign
right there at the bottom.
[DOOR CHIMES]
Okay. Then we give you...
This is your receipt.
Just make sure your party has valid I.D.
when they pick up.
- Anything else?
- MAN: No.
All right. Have a good day.
Can I help you?
Uh, yes.
It'd be wonderful if you could.
I'm, uh, looking for a Werner Ziegler.
Has he been in here in
the last few hours?
I'm s... I'm sorry.
Even if he was here,
it's not company policy
to give out customer information.
Even if he just walked in?
I don't care about what he did.
Well, I really can't.
He is my brother-in-law,
and we're very worried about him.
He has early stage dementia,
and on top of that, he's a diabetic.
He doesn't have his medicine,
and my wife is beside herself.
Oh, no.
Uh, W-We talked long-distance
to their sister, Margarethe,
back in Germany.
She said Werner called
ranting and raving,
wanting her to send money,
and, well, she said she did,
to this branch.
I have his insulin in a
cooler out in the car,
and I was hoping I would
get here ahead of him.
Look, yeah, he was here,
but you missed him.
- He left about an hour ago.
- [SIGHS]
Oh, no, no.
Damn.
Just took the money and left?
Yeah.
Well, not right away.
He made a couple calls on the pay phone,
picked up his money, then left.
And, what, just wandered off on foot?
He got in a car.
Um, I think one of his
calls was for a cab.
You see what company?
- Was it a regular taxi, car service?
- I didn't.
- I'm sorry.
- Mm-hmm.
Any chance that...
that I might have a... a peek
at your security video,
see who got him?
[CHUCKLES] No.
Oh. I get it.
Not company policy.
Then...
could you tell me where
the nearest hospital is?
FRED: He was here a good half-hour or so
before his money order came through.
He asked if his money came, but not yet.
- You mind?
- Oh.
[KEYBOARD SCRAPES]
[TAPE WHIRRING]
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
FRED: Well, that's bad luck.
- You can't see the car.
- Yeah.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Thanks for your help.
Sure.
Good luck. Hope you find him.
[VEHICLES PASSING]
[SIGHS]
Can I see it?
For what it's worth, I believe him.
He said he'd be gone four days.
He's not going to any cops.
This is about him wanting
to see his wife,
plain and simple.
She's on a Lufthansa flight.
Landing in Denver nine hours from now.
[SIGHS] Yeah.
And your men will be there.
And they'll follow her from the airport
to wherever he's holed up.
And then?
There's another way to play this.
If I can find him before
the wife gets here,
let me bring him in and
finish what he started.
His crew can't do it without him.
If Ziegler disappears,
you are left with the most
expensive hole in the ground
this side of the Mississippi.
You can find him?
This is on me. I'll fix it.
♪ ♪
MIKE: Yeah.
You get everybody back in.
Get them on the phone
to every cab company
and car service. You make up a story.
Find out who picked Ziegler up
at the Travel Wire on Fourth.
And start calling hotels...
here, Colorado, Arizona.
He had to register under his own name...
or his wife's.
♪ ♪
Pull the transcript on
the last call to his wife.
♪ ♪
Read it to me.
What'd they talk about?
No. After that.
After the dog.
They were gonna go on vacation.
Baden-Baden.
Natural springs.
♪ ♪
FRED: Hey, there.
Did you find your brother-in-law?
- Is he okay?
- [DOOR CHIMES]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
Yes, I'm calling for one of your guests.
Um, Werner Ziegler.
Right.
Z-I-E-G-L-E-R.
You're sure?
And there's no reservation
under that name?
LALO: [WHISTLING]
♪ Con el amo De la plaza ♪
♪ Hay Que tener más cuidado ♪
♪ Porque lo ven muy tranquilo ♪
[WHISTLING "EL AMO DE LA PLAZA" ]
[ENGINE STARTS]
I won't lie. It's been a tough year.
But I'm proud to say
Hamlin Hamlin McGill
is back and going strong.
It's his lasting legacy,
which is why this couldn't
be more appropriate.
I know this would have
meant the world to him...
a good and proper memorial
for a man who was many things,
but always a lawyer first.
MAN: On behalf of the whole school,
we want to thank you.
Me?
No, I didn't donate any of this.
I'm just a guest.
Really? Dude, I'm pretty
sure I heard someone say
- you paid for all of it.
- Yeah.
Well, I didn't.
I wish I could take credit for it,
but I can't.
♪ ♪
CORDOVA: The invitation
says "anonymous donor."
I assumed that meant HHM.
Huh.
- WOMAN: Baked Brie?
- Don't mind if I do.
[WHISPERING] Actually, I happen to know
Mr. James McGill paid for
the reading room himself.
LYNTON: Really?
The brother did this?
I saw him write the check.
WOMAN: How much do you think this cost?
- Hi, Rich.
- [CHUCKLING] Hey.
This is quite an event.
Looks like half the attorneys
in the southwest are here.
[CHUCKLING] Yeah.
- They all came for Chuck.
- Mm.
I heard someone say
that Jimmy paid for all this himself?
♪ ♪
He'd... prefer to remain anonymous.
Oh. Mm. Mm. Well, where is he?
I was hoping to say hello.
Uh, he's around here somewhere.
♪ ♪
Oh. Isn't that him out there?
Hmm.
I guess even a year out,
an event like this can be tough.
I better go check on him.
- Thanks for coming, Rich.
- Yeah.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
KIM: It's almost time to go back in.
$23,000.
I can't believe I wrote a
$23,000 check for this.
You know?
I don't even see anyone
from the bar association in there.
We still have almost a week.
Someone on the board
will hear about this,
and they'll believe it because...
... they heard it from a colleague.
Yeah, I know. Word gets around, but...
Try this on for size.
Judge Papadoumian is in her chambers.
She's working late.
Everyone else has gone home.
Suddenly, she smells something,
something burning.
She crosses to her door.
It's warm to the touch.
She opens it.
Whoosh! Wall of flames.
Her clerk's chamber's on fire.
And she's trapped. But then,
through the fire and smoke,
a figure emerges. It's Jimmy McGill.
See, I rescue a judge.
Now, that, people are gonna talk about.
And it's... it's too
big, and probably...
it's not how I come
back from "insincere."
Right.
[SIGHS]
Okay.
Wanna go back in, get
your money's worth?
Yeah. I'm starving.
Those little hamburgers
are looking good.
[SIGHS]
I'm allowed to pay for the food,
but I'm too sad to eat.
Z-I-E-G-L-E-R.
He is?
You don't know if he's on the property
at the moment?
No.
No, I don't need to
talk to him right now.
No. No message.
No. Thank you. You have a nice day.
♪ ♪
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[TICKET MACHINE WHIRS, CLICKS]
♪ ♪
[TICKET MACHINE BEEPS]
[TICKET MACHINE WHIRS, CLICKS]
♪ ♪
[ENGINE STARTS]
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[ENGINE REVS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
♪ ♪
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[ENGINE REVS]
♪ ♪
[TICKET MACHINE WHIRS, BEEPS]
Get out of the way! Go!
Sorry. It's just not working.
[SHOUTS IN SPANISH]
- Excuse me.
- Hello?
NOLAN: I'm at the north gate.
And the machine is stuck.
- At which gate?
- The north gate.
[ENGINE REVS]
♪ ♪
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[TIRES SCREECH]
♪ ♪
[BREATHING SHALLOWLY]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[PAPERS RUSTLING]
HAMLIN: All right, if everyone's ready.
Folks, this is Duncan Springer.
He's a senior from Mayfield High School
in Las Cruces.
Duncan, have a seat.
Duncan's editor of the school newspaper,
and his Model UN delegation
represents Kazakhstan.
In fact, Duncan's
delegation was selected
to visit the real UN in New York City.
Duncan, what can you tell us about that?
- Oh, it was...
- This is Marcie Ramirez.
She's from Moriarty High.
Please.
She's captain of the debate team.
What's your strategy gonna be, Marcie?
- I think it'll...
- This is Franklyn Pickett.
He's from Manzano High.
Please have a seat.
Franklyn is school president,
and he wrote a play.
Franklyn, what can you
tell us about your play?
- It's...
- Teodora,
how did you get interested in Ethiopia?
- Well...
- Kristy,
- what's it like working with elders?
- It was...
Raymond, how'd you manage that?
I've...
All right.
Things are becoming much clearer now.
JULIE: Can I let them go?
- Uh, have they had lunch?
- Yes.
Unless there's any additional questions?
Oh, uh, did they all get the...
- Yes, they did.
- Great.
- Thank them again before leaving.
- Of course.
Here's where we are...
Raymond Chin six votes,
Duncan Springer six votes,
Marcie Ramirez five votes,
Franklyn Pickett, Teodora Moon,
and Tristram Bolger three votes each,
and Kristy Esposito one vote.
Well, looks like we have
three scholarships to give
and three front runners.
So, unless there's any disagreement,
- I think we can...
- [CLEARS THROAT]
Uh, Jimmy?
Uh, yeah.
Uh, the one vote for Kristy Esposito?
That was me.
And for what it's worth,
I-I think we should
give her another look.
Esposito?
That's the shoplifter?
The shoplifter.
Ya... That's right.
I mean, her grades are good.
Maybe not quite as good as
some of the other kids,
but they're good.
And her recommendations are solid.
And, yeah, she's had some trouble,
but, um, she was new in town,
and she made some bad choices.
And that was sophomore year.
She's had two really
strong years since then.
And have you all read this?
Her essay is...
well, that experience
is what got her interested in the law.
And it's really good.
It's really good.
And my point is that
maybe someone who's been in trouble,
someone who doesn't
have a perfect record,
you know, who's made mistakes
and faced the consequences...
maybe she brings something
that the others don't.
I think that deserves
real consideration.
Jimmy, you make a hell of an argument.
How about we take another vote?
JIMMY: Kristy! Ms. Esposito, hold up!
Hey. Jimmy McGill.
Hi. We met inside.
Oh. Hi. [CHUCKLES]
Hi.
You didn't get it.
You were never gonna get it.
They...
They dangle these
things in front of you.
They tell you, you got a chance,
but... I'm sorry... it's a lie
because they had already
made up their mind
and they knew what they were gonna do
before you walked in the door.
You made a mistake,
and they are never forgetting it.
As far as they're concerned,
your mistake is just...
it's who you are, and it's all you are.
And I'm not just talking
about the scholarship here.
I'm talking about everything.
I mean, they'll smile at you,
they'll pat you on the head,
but they are never, ever letting you in.
But listen.
Listen.
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't because you don't need them.
They're not gonna give it to you?
So what?
You're gonna take it.
You're gonna do whatever it takes.
Do you hear me?
You are not gonna play by the rules.
You're gonna go your own way.
You're gonna do what they won't do.
You're gonna be smart.
You are gonna cut corners,
and you are gonna win.
They're on the 35th floor?
You're gonna be on the 50th floor.
You're gonna be looking down on them.
And the higher you rise,
the more they're gonna hate you.
Good. Good. You rub their noses in it.
You make them suffer.
You don't matter all that much to them.
So what? So what?
Screw them.
Remember... the winner takes it all.
I've gotta go get my bus.
[CHUCKLES]
You... You understand what I'm
trying to tell you, right?
Yes.
I think I do.
All right.
All right, go get 'em.
[ELEVATOR CHIMES]
[CLEARS THROAT]
[KEYS JANGLE]
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[ENGINE SPUTTERS]
[SIGHS]
[BANGING ON STEERING WHEEL]
Damn it! Damn it! God damn it!
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
[SOBBING]
No.
[CRYING]
[WHIMPERING]
No.
[FIST BANGS] No. No.
[SOBBING CONTINUES]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[DOOR CHIMES]
- FRED: Can I help you?
- Hey.
Uh, my friend was here earlier,
um, bald fellow, about so tall.
Yeah. Did, uh, they find
his brother-in-law?
Is he okay?
No, no.
No, we haven't found him yet.
We're really worried.
- I'm sorry to hear about that.
- Yeah.
So, I was wondering if
there's maybe something
that, you know, my friend missed.
I showed him everything I've got.
Show me what you showed him.
Maybe you should just call your friend.
I did, and, you know,
he told me to come back
and take another look.
I... [SIGHS] I'd really appreciate it.
I can't. I'm sorry.
You better just call the police.
Sure, sure.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Travel Wire. This is Fred.
Fourth street.
Nearest cross street is Lomas.
10:00 p.m. Yeah.
Okay. Have a great day.
Thank you.
[PHONE HANGS UP]
♪ ♪
[CEILING CREAKING]
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
♪ ♪
_
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
♪ ♪
[WATER SPLASHES]
[ICE CUBES CLINKING]
[SLURPS]
[GULPS] Ahh.
[SIGHS]
WOMAN: Is there a Mr. Ziegler here?
Mr. Werner Ziegler?
Oh, uh, yes.
I am Ziegler.
There's a call for you.
Oh. Ja.
Uh, uh... [CHUCKLES]
I will be right there.
Thank you.
[SPEAKING GERMAN] _
LALO: This is Werner?
Yes.
Who is this?
I'm calling on behalf of Gustavo Fring.
[SIGHING]
Ah, yes.
I see.
Is Mr. Fring very upset?
What do you think?
Please let him know the
work will continue.
Did Michael show him my letter?
I explained everything.
Uh, no, Michael hasn't
shared that with Mr. Fring.
The letter has specific instructions.
My men will be able to
continue a few days
without me.
The work will go on.
Ask Michael.
Michael.
Michael's very busy,
and he asked me to speak with you.
Do you remember what
your instructions were?
Certainly.
They are to finish clearing the debris,
then begin the south wall.
That's the south wall?
The south wall, yes.
The concrete is standing by.
They can start pouring.
It's very straightforward,
so Kai will kno...
LALO: The "concrete form"?
Sorry. I didn't get that last part.
Could you repeat that?
Werner?
Mr. Ziegler?
Michael.
Is that you?
[PHONE HANGS UP]
I'm so sorry if I...
Get dressed.
Michael...
I don't wanna hear another
damn word out of you.
Go.
[WATER SPLASHES IN DISTANCE]
[DOOR OPENS, CREAKS]
[KEYS JANGLE]
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
[DOOR CREAKS, SLAMS]
Hey.
- Hey.
- I think I got something here.
Take a look.
The problem might have been
starting with "Remorse,"
so I'm trying to work
into it more gradually.
Uh, "The Law,"
"Plans," then "Remorse,"
then "Brother," then "Legacy."
What do you think?
Everything okay?
Yeah.
How'd it go?
We gave three very bright
young people scholarships.
Good.
All right, we can work on this.
I know it's a lot,
but this is one time you
do not want to wing it.
Yeah.
Jimmy, the hard part's done.
Reading room, scholarship, cemetery.
By now, they've got to have
heard about some of it.
We set up the dominoes,
and now you just knock them down.
[SIGHS]
I can say whatever I want.
To the board, I'm still that guy.
Well, you got to say something.
[SIGHS]
What if, uh...
What if, um...
[BOOK THUDS]
What if Chuck does the talking for me?
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
Wait here.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[LINE RINGING]
- GUS: Yes?
- I got him.
Where are you now?
Out by an old raceway off 55,
about 8 miles north of San Ysidro.
Where was he?
A place called Dulce Vega Hot Springs
up in Jemez.
It's got to be where his wife is headed.
Something else.
Yes?
When I found him, he was on the phone
with an interested party
pretending to be one of your guys.
What did he tell them?
Nothing useful.
- You're certain?
- Yes.
You have any idea who it was?
[SIGHS]
I do.
All right, I'll bring him in now.
No.
Keep him there.
GUS: Wait.
I'd go another way.
That I know.
That'd be a mistake.
This discussion serves no purpose.
Wait where you are.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
I'll take care of it.
Are you sure?
Yes.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[CELLPHONE CLOSES]
God damn it.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[POUNDS ON HOOD]
Get out.
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
I want to know what your end game was.
What did you think was gonna happen?
I thought I would come back
and my friend Michael would
be very, very angry,
but in time,
he would understand and forgive.
It was never up to me.
Oh, Michael, look.
I know I've made trouble for you,
and I'm very sorry for
the damage I caused.
I will repair what I
broke with my own hands,
but, please, Margarethe
will land any minute.
Soon, she will be at the motel.
Please take me back there.
Let us be together for a little, huh?
Let her see me and know
everything is okay.
Ah, please, Michael.
I go back now,
I go back in the morning...
what difference can it make?
It's not gonna happen.
[SCOFFS]
Let me speak to Mr. Fring.
I will explain everything.
I will make him understand.
You're not gonna talk to Fring.
Oh, please. I know if I...
Werner, nothing you can say or do
will make anyone trust you again.
I will go home.
I will never breathe
a word of this ever.
The money... I give all of it back.
I will tell no one.
I s-swear.
It will be as if none
of this ever happened.
Please, Michael.
You know I will keep silent.
You know it. Please.
[SIGHS]
Does your wife have a
cellphone with her?
Yes.
I need you to call her now.
She landed an hour ago.
But she knows nothing.
And you need to keep it that way.
She's being followed.
She's followed?
She goes back to the airport,
nothing will happen to her.
Surely they could not...
they would not...
Hey, pull yourself together.
Give me the phone. I call her now.
- Calm... Calm Dow...
- Give it to me.
Calm down!
She can't suspect.
It doesn't matter what you tell her,
as long as she goes
back where she belongs.
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SPEAKING GERMAN] _
Hello. Ja.
_
[SPEAKING GERMAN] _
_ [SNIFFS]
_
[SPEAKING GERMAN] _
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[SNIFFLES]
Will she do it?
She was very angry,
but, yes, she will go home.
Michael...
if she does not hear a word from me,
she will ask questions.
She will go to the police.
There will be a story, an accident.
Lawyers will visit, German lawyers.
[SIGHS]
Her questions will be answered.
This you swear?
This I swear.
And my men?
They're going home.
They'll be okay. They're trusted.
[BREATHING SHALLOWLY]
Is there no other way, truly?
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
There are so many stars
visible in New Mexico.
I will walk out there...
to get a better look.
[GUNSHOT]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
GALE: Wow.
I mean...
it's incredible.
I feel like we've been
talking about this forever,
and now...
here it is.
An architectural feat.
Truly.
Herculean.
This is...
Yeah!
[CHUCKLES]
I can work with this.
I mean, it's not exactly
what we talked about,
but it has possibilities,
even unfinished.
Uh, ventilation at this
point is the main hurdle,
but with a series of fans
and the right equipment,
I am certain that I could
do a rudimentary cook
at the very least.
Not until it is ready.
Oh.
Um, of course.
We only want to do it
if it's done right.
I was just... exploring possibilities.
I am gonna go up and check the...
Okay.
[FOOTSTEPS CLUNKING]
Oh. Hello.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
MAN: Of course.
That won't be a problem.
Where do you have it?
Okay.
This should do it.
Chuck wrote a good letter, huh?
Chuck wrote a great letter.
It's not just the words,
though, you know?
It's how you read them.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Jimmy, whatever happens in there...
I'm with you.
WOMAN: Mr. McGill, we've
reviewed all the facts,
the same facts as the hearing committee.
We've evaluated their findings.
All that's left is for us to hear
your prepared statement.
So, whenever you're ready.
JIMMY: Thank you, Your Honor.
I-I don't have a prepared statement.
But I do have this.
Um, it's a letter
from my brother, Charles McGill.
He left it to me in his will,
and I received it last
year after he passed.
[CLEARS THROAT]
"Dear Jimmy,
I have left many things unsaid
in our relationship through the years.
Rather than allow
these unspoken thoughts to die with me,
I've chosen to record them here for you.
I hope you will take my words
in the spirit in which
they are intended.
I remember quite clearly
the day you came home from the hospital.
You can't imagine the joy on Mom's face.
I can honestly say I
never saw her happier."
[PAPER RUSTLING]
I'm sorry. I can't do this.
I was...
I was just gonna try to...
I was gonna try to move you all
with my brother's eloquent words,
you know, pull on your heartstrings,
but it's not right.
This letter's between me and him,
and it should stay that way.
Listen, my brother, Chuck...
you... you knew him.
He loved me in his own way.
He loved me as a brother.
He did not love me as a lawyer.
Big reason I became a lawyer was Chuck.
He was the most brilliant
man I ever knew.
And an incredible lawyer.
You know?
And, uh, he knew exactly
who he was... exactly.
And all my life, I wanted
to make him proud.
And he was not an easy man
to make proud, you know?
Like climbing Everest without supplies.
If you were one of the lucky
few who reached that peak,
even for a moment, if
you made him proud,
wow, what a feeling.
Whew.
And he let you know it, too.
But if you weren't one
of those people...
he was polite enough,
but he did not suffer fools, you know?
And he could be
judgmental and difficult.
And he knew how to get under your skin.
And... could be a real son of a bitch.
[CHUCKLES]
Chuck was the one who
was always right...
always.
And usually he was.
You know?
So, for a guy like me...
[SIGHS]
I did lousy in school.
I lacked ambition.
I always cut corners. I mean, for me
to live up to the standards
of Charles McGill...
[CHUCKLES]
I mean, look at me.
I'll never be as moral as him.
I'll never be as smart.
I'll never be as respected.
I'll never be as good as Chuck.
[SNIFFS]
But I can try.
I can try.
If you decide, and I
get to be a lawyer...
... I'll do everything in my power
to be worthy of the name McGill.
And if you decide I'm not a lawyer...
... doesn't matter.
I'll still try to be the
best man that I can be.
I'm lucky.
I got this letter.
I never had a chance
to write him a letter
and to tell him all the
things that I should have.
And I got to believe that somehow...
... somehow he knows.
Oh, that's...
That'll have to do it for me.
Sorry.
Thank you.
I knew you could do it! I
knew you had it in you.
- That was so great.
- I mean, yes. They...
They have to reinstate you, right?
- They just have to.
- Uh, yeah. Did you see those suckers?
That one asshole was crying.
He had actual tears!
Jesus, Kim!
Listen, I started reading the letter,
and I just knew it wasn't...
I could tell by their faces
it wasn't gonna be enough, right?
So I just went off on
this flow, you know?
I had this energy going through me.
It was like improv or jazz, and then...
boom! I sunk the hook in!
I am so lucky I have this letter.
God, I could see the Matrix, you know?
I was invincible.
I could dodge bullets, baby.
And you were right. You were right.
It was all about Chuck the whole time.
Oh, Mr. McGill, you're still here.
There's some good news.
- JIMMY: Believe me, I already know.
- Oh, good.
Then if you want to come
with me to the office,
there's some paperwork for you to sign.
Absolutely. Let's do this thing.
Oh, and, sweetheart,
I'm gonna need one more form... a DBA...
because I'm not gonna be practicing
under the name McGill, so...
Shouldn't be a problem.
Just down the hall, we
have all the forms.
- Great. Great.
- Wait. Wh... Wait.
Jimmy, Jimmy, what?
S'all good, man.
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --