Previously on "Better Call Saul"...
I think he did what he did because of me.
Well, Howard, I guess
that's your cross to bear.
I was thinking that maybe you
should talk to someone.
- A shrink?
- Kevin figures we'll file
for federal charter.
Just observing.
You brought me because you have an ask.
Tell me about the job.
SAUL: You're looking
at Albuquerque's newest
mobile communications specialist.
Cellphone sales.
Strictly gainful employment.
And 10 months from now,
I'm a lawyer again.
[SHREDDER WHIRRING]
[THUMPING]
[GRUNTING]
SAUL: Unh! Damn it.
[THUMPING CONTINUES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTING] Come on.
[WHIRRING CONTINUES]
Unh! This is the one!
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS] Jackpot!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[WHIRRING CONTINUES]
It's all here.
FRANCESCA: Meaning what, exactly?
Meaning, uh, you know, field mice,
and, you know, you got
your nest-building squirrel.
You got your... Whatever.
Three cheers for morality.
Hey, where's the, uh... What?
You know, the...
Use your words.
Aha.
[BOX CUTTER CLICKS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[WHIRRING CONTINUES]
[BOX CUTTER SCRAPING]
[GRUNTING]
Did you shred the files under your desk?
Yes.
- Okay.
- [BOX CUTTER SCRAPING]
[GRUNTING]
What about your Rolodex?
Yes, and everything
in the filing cabinets
- and the safe and...
- The stuff in the bathroom.
You did that yourself, remember?
Right, right.
[BOX CUTTER SCRAPING]
[GRUNTING]
[WHIRRING CONTINUES]
[WHIRRING STOPS]
[PANTING]
All right, that's it.
I'm going. Do me a favor.
Take those with you.
Drop them off at least five miles
from here... in separate Dumpsters.
[PANTING]
[STAMMERS]
Oh, right. Um...
[PANTING]
Fine.
Okay, when the cops come talk to you...
and they will...
what are you gonna tell them?
"Talk to my attorney."
Yeah.
Tell 'em, uh, Jimmy sent ya. Okay?
And where are you gonna be
November 12th at 3:00 p.m.?
I'll be there,
but if it doesn't ring
at 3:00 on the dot, I'm gone.
Don't worry. It's gonna ring.
Well, I guess, uh...
that's it.
[CHUCKLES]
Quite a ride, huh?
[SCOFFS]
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
Yep.
[DOOR CREAKS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[DRAWER OPENS]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
I need a new dust filter
for my Hoover Max Extract
Pressure Pro, model 60.
Can you help me with that?
Pickup.
How hot? Red hot.
I know where that is.
I'll be there.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[CELLPHONE SNAPS]
[PANTING]
♪
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
♪
♪ Now that we're here together ♪
♪ Even the nights are better ♪
♪
♪ Poses to remember, let's just... ♪
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT SINGING]
[SOFT BOSSA NOVA MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ Something that I found ♪
♪ I don't mind
as long as you're with me ♪
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
♪ I don't mind ♪
♪ If the world is feeling off ♪
♪ I thank just the seven seas ♪
♪ There are times we'll find ♪
[GEARSHIFT CLICKS, ENGINE RUMBLES]
[BRAKES SQUEAL, ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
♪ I don't mind as long
as you're with me ♪
[VEHICLE DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
- Yep. [CLEARS THROAT]
- [DOOR OPENS, DINGS]
Maximum privacy.
It's the best money can buy.
10? No. Can't do it.
Everyone wants these things.
6? Um, yeah. Yeah, I can do 6.
Okay. See you later.
♪ Ohh, ohh ♪
[CELLPHONE SNAPS]
Welcome to CC Mobile.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What can I do for you?
♪ ...there with me ♪
So, privacy sold here?
Yep. This is the place.
Privacy from who?
- Come on. You know.
- ♪ I don't mind ♪
Like, the government?
Could be.
Like the IRS?
Bingo!
So...
So, uh, say you got
a cash-based business.
Like a contracting business?
Contracting. Could be. Could be.
Maybe you don't report
every single penny.
I mean, who does, right?
How are you doing that business?
On the phone.
How are you scheduling appointments?
How are you arranging payments?
On the phone.
And who's listening? That's right.
They know every lick and tittle.
So, you're living your life
free and easy,
and then one day,
at a time of their choosing...
bam! they bring the hammer
down to Chinatown.
- Jesus.
- Jesus is right.
I'm telling you,
these guys don't fool around.
And they will clean your bones
faster than a school of piranhas.
I'll tell you what I do.
I practice something we call
information hygiene.
[INDISTINCT SINGING]
Can't be traced.
Can't be tracked.
That'll keep you clean as a whistle.
What they don't know can't hurt you,
especially if you use it only once per.
You know, that's kind of key.
"Once per"?
Once per what?
Once per week,
once per day, once per call.
I mean, depends on
the nature of your situation.
[SCOFFS] How much are they?
They're cheaper than an audit,
guaranteed.
Unfortunately...
What?
Well, this one's spoken for.
My supply is very short.
Well, people are gobbling
these up like Tic Tacs.
[PRINTER WHIRS, PAPER TEARS]
[DRAWER CLOSES]
Thanks again.
Tell your friends.
[DOOR OPENS, DINGS]
[AIR HISSES]
[AIRPLANE PASSING]
[CAR ALARM CHIRPS]
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
[KEYPAD BEEPS] [FRENCH ACCENT] Hello?
MIKE: Welcome to the USA.
Use the prepaid parking ticket
in the cup holder to exit the lot.
Make a right.
Follow the signs for I-70 west.
- Got it?
- 70 headed west. Yes.
Keep the phone close by,
and I'll call you in about 20 minutes
and talk you through
the rest of it, okay?
I understand. Yes.
[AIRPLANE PASSING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[GEARSHIFT CLICKS]
[BIRD CAWING]
[CELLPHONE RINGS]
- [KEYPAD BEEPS]
- Yes.
I'm here, mark 238,
but there's nobody here.
You need to relieve yourself?
No.
- Where are you?
- You sure?
Because if you do,
I suggest you do it now.
You're not going to have
another chance for awhile.
As I said, I'm fine.
Suit yourself.
Pop the trunk. Inside, you'll see a hood.
Take it out. Close the trunk.
Place your luggage next to you,
and put the hood on.
That clear?
You want me to stand here
with a hood on my head?
Those are the rules.
[LINE DISCONNECTS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[TRUNK CLOSES]
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
[CAR ALARM CHIRPS]
[SIGHS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
[DOOR SLIDES OPEN]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACH]
Step forward.
[POUNDING ON PARTITION]
We're gonna hit some rough road.
There's a strap for you to hold on to
if you reach out to your left.
You want some water?
No, thanks.
[CLANGING]
[VEHICLES PASSING]
[BELL DINGING]
[HORNS HONKING]
[GRAVEL CRUNCHING]
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
Step down. Then walk.
[VEHICLE DOOR CLOSES]
There are stairs.
Step up.
Forward.
That's good.
Right there.
Whew!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
So, where, exactly?
The entrance will be back there.
You need to stay within
the footprint of the building.
[SCANNER BEEPS]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[BUTTON CLICKS, SCANNER BEEPS]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[SCANNER BEEPING]
[WATER DRIPPING]
All right.
You can do it?
Absolutely. [CHUCKLES]
How long will it take?
I want to say seven months,
but I think I could do it in six.
Even with blasting?
The geologist's report was very thorough,
and with the right equipment,
modern methods,
blasting will be quite unnecessary...
assuming your employer
is willing to meet my price.
Price isn't an issue.
Copy That.
So, 56 feet down with no blasting,
working nights only,
you're saying seven months, max?
My men and I dug a tunnel under
the border into downtown El Paso
3/4 of a kilometer long, undetected.
That took us 17 weeks.
If I can do that,
I can certainly do this.
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
Yeah?
Mm-hmm.
Yep.
That's what I thought.
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
Thank you for your time.
Pardon?
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[GROANS LIGHTLY]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[PAPER RUSTLING]
[KIM SIGHS]
Pull the short end.
[GASPS] It's too tight. Live with it.
Where do you look when
the judge is talking to you?
In the eyes.
And what do you call the judge?
- "Sir"?
- "Ma'am."
Or, better still, "Your Honor."
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
Sit over there. And leave that alone.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Not guilty? You can't be serious.
On what planet
would you take this to trial?
You should work with me on this one.
The kid threw a cinder block
through a jewelry-store window,
and I have a witness.
Frankly, I'm being generous.
I want six months probation,
time served, no jail.
And I want to win the lottery
and breed labradoodles.
Nice try, Bill.
You're not gonna get away with it.
Away with what?
Come on.
You're not gonna play dumb, are you?
Please enlighten me.
The arresting officers took the
first part of my guy's statement
before he was Mirandized.
They collected evidence
based on that interview,
and you knew all about it.
That's irrelevant.
How would you... Why would you even...
Your guy did it.
Bill, you don't want me
to bring this up with the judge.
Not only will your case be DOA,
but she will rip you a new one
on the record.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
- The judge is not buying any of that.
- I think she will.
It's all right here.
Listen, I...
[SIGHS]
Okay. 10 months jail.
6 months probation, time served.
This kid needs a chance
to turn his life around,
not rot in prison and join a gang.
Are you joking?
We started at 18 months jail.
Up to you.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[PAPER RUSTLING]
Eight months jail.
Four months probation.
- Wait. What happened to six?
- You're annoying me.
You can't play chicken with me.
I invented chicken.
[DOOR OPENS]
Wow. Okay.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[EXHALING SHARPLY]
Fine.
[SIGHS]
Six months jail time, one year probation.
I can't make four months fly.
It's impossible, completely impossible.
You don't have time for this.
Bill, I only have one other client,
and it's a bank.
I have all the time in the world.
- [DOOR OPENS]
- BAILIFF: All rise
for the Honorable Judge Lipitz.
[DOOR CLOSES]
WOMAN: The judge.
MAN: Yeah.
WOMAN: CR2003114721...
- Fine.
- Four months.
Four months probation?
...State versus David Estrada.
- Yes.
- Good morning.
Please be seated.
If I may, Your Honor.
Yes, Ms. Wexler.
I'm happy to say
the defense and prosecution
have reached an agreement.
- Hey, wait. No. Stand still.
- [ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
This is mine, remember?
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Um, I don't mean to rush you,
but the meeting's in 15,
and with traffic...
Okay. Got it. Thanks.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
I'm gonna have
a probation officer on my ass
for fourth months?
David, listen to me.
Here's what you're gonna do.
Today, after you leave here,
you will go straight to
your grandfather's restaurant,
and you will beg him for a job, any job.
If he tells you to scrub
the grill, you scrub the grill.
If he tells you to clean the toilet,
you clean the toilet.
You will show up on time.
You will smile.
You will say "please" and "thank you."
You will keep your nose clean.
You understand?
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
Because if you don't,
you will go to jail.
Grown-up jail with grown-up bad guys.
Picture that, David.
Really picture it.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS,
TELEPHONE RINGS]
And know this...
I'm not gonna do
a damn thing about it next time.
You got it?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
JIMMY: Nope. No.
Uh... no. Nope.
Wait. Wait. Hey, look.
"Doctor Zhivago" is about to start.
Lots of attractive men in the snow.
That's your favorite genre.
- [SIGHS]
- Mm. I'm sorry.
I can't.
I have tons of Mesa Verde to catch up on.
Isn't that why you have a paralegal?
Well, I have to review her work.
[CHUCKLES] You watch.
Thanks.
[SIGHS]
Can you work with the TV on?
I have tremendous powers
of concentration.
[BOOK THUDS]
Go ahead. It's fine.
["MAIN TITLE" FROM
"DOCTOR ZHIVAGO" PLAYING]
♪
[TV TURNS OFF]
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
It wasn't bothering me.
[INHALES SHARPLY] Yeah, I know.
I just, uh,
realized there's something
I need to to do at work.
At 9:00 at night? [CHUCKLES]
Yeah, well, it's my first week, you know?
I want to make a good impression.
I'm just getting the hang
of the system, so...
Okay. I'll just go in the bedroom.
Absolutely not. You have work.
I have work. It's okay.
[SIGHS] Okay.
It's all good. Don't wait up.
[DOOR CREAKS, CLOSES]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[DRAWER OPENS, PRINTER WHIRS]
[DRAWER CLOSES]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[DRAWER OPENS, PRINTER WHIRS]
[PAPER TEARS, DRAWER CLOSES]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[DRAWER OPENS, PRINTER WHIRS]
[PAPER TEARS, DRAWER CLOSES]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[DRAWER OPENS, PRINTER WHIRS]
[PAPER TEARS, DRAWER CLOSES]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[DRAWER OPENS, PRINTER WHIRS]
[PAPER TEARS, DRAWER CLOSES]
[PAPER TEARS]
[VEHICLES PASSING]
[DOOR BEEPS]
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
Hey! How's it going?
How you guys set for phones?
We got phones.
Private phones.
Beat it, narc.
Oh, come on.
Would a narc drive this piece of shit?
Take it back to impound, narc.
- [CHUCKLES]
- [SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
Loser.
[TIRES SCREECH]
[RANDY CRAWFORD AND THE
CRUSADERS' "STREET LIFE" PLAYS]
♪ I play the street life ♪
♪ Because there's no place I can go ♪
♪ Street life ♪
♪ It's the only life I know ♪
♪ And there's a thousand parts to play ♪
♪ Street life ♪
♪ Until you play your life away ♪
♪ You let the people see
just who you wanna be ♪
♪ And every night, you shine
just like a superstar ♪
♪ That's how the life is played ♪
♪ A 10-cent masquerade ♪
♪ You dress, you walk, you talk ♪
♪ You're who you think you are ♪
♪ Street life ♪
♪ You can run away from time ♪
♪ For a nickel or a dime ♪
♪ Street life ♪
♪ But you better not get old ♪
[HORN HONKS]
♪ Or you're gonna feel the cold ♪
♪ Ohh ♪
♪
♪ Street life ♪
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
♪ Ohh, street life ♪
Later.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
MAN: Wait up, man.
[ENGINES RUMBLING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
♪
[ENGINES SHUT OFF]
[SIGHS]
♪
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
WOMAN: This one?
MAN: Yeah, no fat boy's
supposed to ride like that.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Hi. How are you?
[CLEARS THROAT]
That's a beautiful ride.
Hey. How's it going?
Did you get, uh...
Did you get that ink in Los Lunas?
[SNIFFLES]
Las Cruces.
Off by one.
And you've been inside?
No, I haven't had the honor,
but I used to be a lawyer.
Emphasis on "used to be."
And I helped a lot of gentlemen
such as yourself...
and your friends here.
And one thing I learned
from working with my clients
in the New Mexico corrections system
is that private conversations
are few and far between.
The man is always
listening on those land lines.
So word to the wise...
uh, if you want to talk
to your friends on the inside,
there is a simple solution.
Yeah? What's that?
This little baby.
It's the most compact model
on the market.
It could be hidden
in any number of places.
And if you buy it from me with cash,
it's completely untraceable.
How much?
[ENGINES REVVING]
Keep the rubber side down!
[KEYS JINGLE]
[LOCK DISENGAGES]
Sorry, guys. You had your chance.
I'm all sold out.
Give me your money.
I'm a narc, remember?
No. We saw you got cash.
- Hand it over.
- Nice try.
Look, Pee Wee, Scooter, Skippy,
it was very good to meet you boys.
Good look with
the junior achievement project.
I-I got to go.
Hey. Hey!
[GRUNTING]
Hey!
[GRUNTS]
Ohh!
Aah! Ohh! Aah!
Aah! Get it.
Go. Go. Go.
Come on, man.
Ugh!
[COUGHS]
[EXHALING SHARPLY]
[COUGHING]
[PANTING]
[WATER RUNNING]
[DOOR CREAKS]
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to wake you.
It's okay.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
What happened?
I got mugged.
Jesus, that's cold.
So? Keep it on there.
Are you sure
you don't want to go to the E.R.
- just to be safe?
- No, I'm fine, really.
What are you doing?
I'm checking that your pupils
are the same size.
I'm okay. I swear.
[DRAWER CLOSES]
[GRUNTS] Sorry.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[GASPS] Whew.
[CHUCKLES]
Look at us.
We're like a Mathew Brady photo.
[LAUGHS]
Yeah. I think you'd need
a cannon to really sell that.
[CHUCKLES]
So, this happened at The Dog House?
Yeah.
At 1:30 in the morning?
Um... I lost track of time.
Mm.
And, uh, parked too far away, so...
[CLICKS TONGUE] It was just dumb.
Did you call the police?
Nah. What's the point?
Anyway, I don't feel like
spending the rest of the night downtown
looking at mug shots
of kids with stringy hair.
What the hell's the matter with me?
It sounds like you were just
in the wrong place at the wrong time.
Back in the day, I would have spotted
those low-rent little skeeves
from a mile away,
and they would have known not to roll me.
Yeah? How would they have known that?
I don't. Just...
Well, [SIGHS] because back then, uh...
I guess I was one of them.
[CHUCKLES]
Well, those days are over.
Yeah.
But, uh...
[SIGHS]
What?
You know what?
Um, I think tomorrow
I might, uh, call that shrink.
Couldn't hurt, right?
No. Couldn't hurt.
[SIGHS]
[INDISTINCT SINGING]
[MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYING]
[CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOFT-ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ I don't mind ♪
[MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENGINE RUMBLING]
[POUNDING ON GATE]
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
Denise!
It's Kim Wexler!
[DOOR OPENS]
Denise, why are you still here?
You were supposed to meet me
in court an hour ago.
DENISE: So, I missed it, right?
Not yet.
I got the clerk to push your hearing,
but we've got to go now.
I can't.
I'm freaking out.
I'm sorry, Ms. Wexler,
but I can't go to jail.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[SIGHS]
I can't promise you no jail time.
But what I do know for sure
is that if you don't
come with me right now to court,
the judge is gonna issue a bench warrant,
and then jail is a done deal.
[CELLPHONE VIBRATES]
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
Denise, you can do this.
It's your first offense.
It was under two ounces.
Trust me. I'm good at this.
Why don't you change into something nice.
We'll do this together.
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[CELLPHONE VIBRATING]
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
Hi, Paige.
PAIGE: Kim, we've got a huge problem.
There's a major error
in the branch paperwork
that went out to Denver and Flagstaff.
It has to be fixed ASAP.
Unfortunately, I'm right
in the middle of something,
but I can be there at 4:00.
- I need you now.
- Oh, I'm sorry. I can't.
I don't know what to tell you, Paige.
I just... Not right now.
- But, Kim, this is...
- I'm sorry.
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
Denise, it's time!
Come on! We got to go!
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
You look great.
Thanks.
[GATE CREAKS]
All right. Let's go get 'em.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS,
TELEPHONE RINGING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[WATER BUBBLING]
Paige, I'm so sorry.
- Let's get this fixed right now.
- It's fixed.
I had to pull everyone on the floor
to re-type and proof the submission
because we didn't have the files
and your paralegal
didn't know where they were.
I'd really like to apologize
to Kevin personally, as well,
if he's available.
He's not.
Let me be very clear.
The mistake is not the issue here.
Everyone makes mistakes.
But I need to know your head is in this.
You made us a promise
that Mesa Verde would be your sole focus.
When we need you, we need you.
We're not a client you hang up on.
I'm really sorry, Paige.
It'll never happen again.
I hope not.
[FOOTSTEPS DEPARTING]
[TELEPHONE RINGING,
INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[WATER BUBBLING]
[GROANING]
[SPEAKING GERMAN]
Speak English, please.
[GERMAN ACCENT] I'm going to throw up.
[GROANS] I suggest you don't.
Now, hold on. We're almost there.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GROANS LIGHTLY]
Thank you.
Ahh.
[PANTING]
You okay?
[SIGHS]
Better.
[GAGS, BURPS]
Pardon.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
I take the Dramamine,
but it doesn't help.
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
Okay.
[TOOLS CLATTERING]
[SNIFFLES, EXHALES SHARPLY]
[SNIFFLES]
Over there?
Over there.
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[METAL CLICKING]
[PEN SCRATCHING]
[EXHALING SHARPLY]
[SPEAKING GERMAN]
[SIGHS]
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
So?
Hmm?
Before I can begin excavation,
I must support the existing structure
to avoid a cave-in.
Normally, this would involve
the piling rig,
working from above.
But there can be no activity
visible from the surface, hmm?
[WATER DRIPPING]
So I must construct secant walls
of CFA piles,
working completely underground.
[SPEAKING GERMAN]
Um, difficult.
Next, I must somehow place I-beams
across the top of the secant walls
to support the floor and the machinery.
[LIPS POPPING]
Excuse me.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Only now can I fully excavate.
I will need to move perhaps
1,700 cubic meters of dirt.
That means trucking out about 200 loads.
[WATER DRIPPING]
Going this deep, we will surely hit rock,
which means blasting.
[IMITATES EXPLOSION]
[SIGHS]
I will need schematics
of utility in the area.
You'll get those.
Once the space is fully cleared,
I can waterproof,
then fabricate casts
for the retaining walls
and pour concrete.
We would need, uh...
[CHUCKLES] About 150 cubic meters.
This is just the beginning.
And all this in complete secrecy.
Judging from the sounds I heard,
I assume we are not far from a town.
This is also not... optimal.
A project like this,
many, many things can go wrong.
[DOOR OPENS]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
So, it's impossible?
Dangerous, difficult,
and very, very expensive...
not quite impossible.
Gustavo Fring.
[SPEAKING GERMAN] _
[CHUCKLES]
[SPEAKING GERMAN]
[WAND SQUEALING]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
You're good.
[MONITOR BEEPS]
[METAL CLINKING] See you, Marty.
See you, Jimmy.
- Ready for me?
- Okay, next.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[WATER RUNNING, DOOR CREAKS]
- [WATER STOPS]
- Howard.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Everything okay?
Everything's fine.
And how are you doing?
I've been better.
I'm heading up to the D.A.'s
office for my PPD check-in,
so, you know...
Yeah.
Anyway...
[WATER RUNNING]
[WATER STOPS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
You sure you're okay?
I'm supposed to be in court in, uh...
about 25 minutes.
Big case?
Not particularly.
So, what's up?
[SIGHS] Nothing.
Just...
[CHUCKLES]
You ever have insomnia?
Not really.
Wouldn't wish it on my worst enemy.
Oof.
Don't they have pills for that?
[CHUCKLES]
[SIGHS] I'm... I'm sorry.
I got to ask.
Um, what's... what's eating you?
Jimmy...
I think I've shared enough...
more than enough.
Let's leave it at that. [SNIFFLES]
[GARBAGE CAN CLANGS]
I get it.
You know what, Howard?
Uh, you do yourself a favor,
and you go see someone.
I actually have the number of a shrink.
I got it for a client.
And he's supposed to be great.
I think, um,
I got it right here, actually.
Uh, thanks.
I'm already seeing someone.
Really?
Twice a week.
Is he any good?
Yes.
[SIGHS]
Good seeing you, Howard.
You too.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[SIGHS]
[TOILET FLUSHES]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
[PRINTER WHIRRING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[TELEPHONES RINGING]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
WOMAN: Can you hold, please?
Thank you.
MAN: Uh, yes, sir,
this is, uh, Steve Carlton...
So, where were we?
Community service.
Community service. Right.
Well, it looks like
you completed your hours.
Yep.
Your PPD fees are up to date.
And you've recently procured
lawful employment at...
CC Mobile.
Address?
8351 Louisiana Boulevard.
8351 Louisiana.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
How many hours a week?
This week, uh, 31, but I'll pick up more.
Next month, bring pay stubs.
Will do.
Are you associating
with any known criminals?
No.
All right.
Month two looks good.
Have you thought about
what you're gonna do
once your PPD is up?
I have some plans.
Okay.
Such as...
Until then, I'll show up here
every second Monday of the month
like clockwork.
I'm gonna keep my job
at the cellphone store,
and in 9 months and 24 days,
I will get my law license back.
My partner and I will get a new office.
It'll be like it was,
but bigger and better.
Everything will be better.
I'm gonna have more clients.
I'm gonna win more cases.
I'm gonna be a damn good lawyer,
- and people are gonna know about it.
- Okay.
So... lawyer.
Yeah.
Lawyer.
[SIGHS]