Previously on "Better Call Saul"...
It's territory, isn't it?
The cartel can't give
it to the Salamancas,
so I think they gave it to you.
You have more to do.
We are not even halfway done.
- They need fresh air and, uh...
- Rest and relaxation.
I would help people myself if I could.
Yep.
How can you justify
giving Babineaux 18 months?
Our only witness is a
scumbag disbarred lawyer!
If you say this is the only
way we can legitimately do this,
it's the only way.
KIM: Jimmy, whatever
you're doing, don't.
I have a better way.
[TRUNK POPS]
[SIGHS]
I think I got everything.
If I forgot anything,
I'll just, uh, figure it out on the way.
You're back on Thursday?
Thursday, yeah, unless
we break down in Amarillo.
[VEHICLES PASSING]
[KEYS CLACK, TRUNK CLOSES]
Kim, I want you to know, um,
I don't take this for granted.
It means a lot.
[AIR BRAKE HISSES IN DISTANCE]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
I'll see ya Thursday.
[KEYS CLACK]
[BUS ENGINE REVS]
[LES MCCANN'S "BURNIN' COAL" PLAYS]
[VEHICLE PASSES]
[SIGHS]
♪♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
[PAPER RIPS]
♪♪
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[PENCIL SCRATCHING]
MAN: Can I sit here?
Uh... sure, man.
Uh, just a word of warning...
uh, I had a pile of cheese chili fries
back at Stuckey's with onions on top.
The last guy who sat here
didn't last five miles,
but, uh, yeah, you're welcome to it.
Ah, Jynetta.
[CHUCKLES] Very nice.
I like the hearts over the i's.
- It's a real nice touch.
- Thank you.
- Ahhh, how many we got?
- 10.
10.
[PAPER RUSTLES] All righty.
Would you like to do some postcards?
It's 50 cents per.
Yeah.
- Different pens, please.
- Okay.
♪♪
Oh, Bubba.
[CHUCKLING] Hey.
Uh, okay. [SMACKS LIPS] I
like your passion, but, uh,
just maybe tone down the anger.
Make it that you're... you're sad
that you even have to write the letter.
"I couldn't believe people
could be so heartless
till I heard about you," okay?
Okay. Yeah, I gotchu.
- JIMMY: How many have we got?
- Five.
All right.
Would you like another batch?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
All right.
Different, uhh, pens.
♪♪
Uh, Chastity, let's see what you've got.
Uh, don't...
don't use, uh, swears.
I thought we talked about respect.
We're gonna have to lose that one.
[AIR HISSES]
♪♪
[ENGINE REVS]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
[DOG BARKS]
[DOORBELL JINGLES]
[FLAGPOLE CLACKING]
[ZYDECO MUSIC PLAYS ON STEREO]
[VEHICLE APPROACHES]
[GEAR SHIFT CLICKS]
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF, MUSIC STOPS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[TRUCK DOOR CLOSES]
[VEHICLE PASSES]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[DOORBELL JINGLES]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[DOG WHIMPERS]
[DOOR CLOSES, BELLS JINGLE]
[DOG SNIFFING]
[DOG BARKS IN DISTANCE]
♪♪
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
[SIZZLING, METAL CLANGING]
[MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS, MAN
SINGS IN SPANISH ON RADIO]
♪♪
[VEHICLE PASSES]
I'm a little light, yo.
Couldn't do nothing about it.
Some dumbass festival over at
the fairground, Indian shit.
Five-o was all over.
Well, not real five-o...
like, the rentals.
But you can't sell in
front of them, neither.
We gonna make you right next time.
You're goddamn right you will.
For sure. Next week.
[RUBBER BAND SNAPS]
[SINGING AND MUSIC CONTINUE]
♪♪
[POKER CHIP CLACKS] Hey.
Come here.
- Nacho, man, I got to gettin'...
- Shh, shh, shh.
Just come here.
♪♪
[CHAINS CLINKING]
What's, uh... what's up?
[FOOD SIZZLING]
♪♪
[TABLE CREAKS]
[CHAINS CLINKING]
- [FLESH TEARS]
- Aah!
Shit.
[GROANING]
[EARRING CLATTERS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪♪
[NAPKINS RUSTLE]
What you owe, you owe. With interest.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[DOOR OPENS, VEHICLE PASSES]
[DOOR CREAKS, CLOSES]
[DISHES CLANKING]
♪♪
You had to do that, man.
Guy's not gonna learn otherwise.
Mm-hmm.
So, why didn't you do it?
♪♪
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
MAN: What up, Domingo?
♪♪
[TABLE THUDS LIGHTLY]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[GEARSHIFT CLICKS, ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[VEHICLES PASSING IN DISTANCE]
[KEYS CLACKING]
WOMAN ON TV: ... this can
include headache, nausea,
dizziness, and vision changes.
MAN ON TV: The committee
is the proper place...
[MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYING, SIREN WAILING]
NARRATOR ON TV: But she wasn't
the only witness that...
- [EERIE MUSIC PLAYS]
- [KEYS CLACKING]
[TV CHATTER]
[EXPLOSION]
- ... and I just want to show you the real...
- [DOOR OPENS]
And if you want to
use the scrub, too...
[DOOR CLOSES]
It's just that simple.
[SNIFFS] Mmm. Smells like fresh
lavender, too, ladies, and...
Hey, baby. You're in early.
You in for the night?
Want us to make you some dinner?
... takes the color right out
and this bottle has smoothing agents
that protect your skin
while exfoliating...
[BAG THUDS] Thanks, babe.
Are you gonna smoke with us?
Look at that! This is the best.
It's just... Well, I
think that's incredible,
and I cannot believe
we're still offering this
for under $70...
[TV CHATTER]
- [DOOR OPENS]
- [DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS]
[DOOR CLOSES, LOCK ENGAGES]
[SIGHS]
[JACKET THUDS]
[GUN THUDS, PAPER RUSTLES]
[SHIRT THUDS]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[KEYS JANGLE, LOCK DISENGAGES]
[DOOR SQUEAKS]
[SNIFFS]
[DIAL CLICKING]
♪♪
[LOCK DISENGAGES]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[PAPER RUSTLES, THUDS]
♪♪
[SNIFFS]
[OBJECT CLATTERS]
[SIGHS]
♪♪
[PLASTIC THUDS]
[SIGHS]
♪♪
[PLASTIC SCRAPES]
[SIGHS]
♪♪
[DOOR SLAMS, LOCK ENGAGES]
[HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO]
♪♪
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING, CHEERING]
[MEN CHEER]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
♪♪
[MEN CHEER]
[LAUGHTER]
[CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE]
♪♪
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS,
BILLIARD BALLS CLACKING]
[MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYING,
INDISTINCT SINGING]
Did you know, Michael, my
father was also engineer.
Yeah.
Worked from the day
he could hold a hammer.
Learned the work from doing the work.
Hands like knots of a tree.
[BILLIARD BALLS CLACK, GLASS CLINKS]
You see over there?
He built that.
♪♪
The Sydney Opera House?
Those concrete arches...
impossible in 1957.
Six years it took to
solve the problem... six...
and years more to pour correctly.
To that, my father
gave 10 years of life.
Another stout?
Uh, you know, could I get the, uh...
the "Heefiweesen" this time.
- Oh! [CHUCKLES]
- Sure.
Uh, no, sir, please.
Uh, it's "Hefeweizen."
Oh, I'm sorry. How d'you say it?
Hefeweizen.
Vollkom richtig.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Ah, uh... it's on me.
Oh. Thanks, man.
♪♪
Prost.
Where was I? Ah, the opera.
It's for the ages.
For my father, it was his achievement,
a creation that will endure.
[TAPPING ON GLASS]
Ja.
[INHALES DEEPLY] What
about you, Michael?
Your papa... what did he do?
[SCOFFS]
My dad?
Oh...
left behind a cold-water
flat and a stack of bills.
That's about all.
WERNER: Ah, not true.
He also left you, Michael.
You are his legacy.
[LAUGHS]
Yeah.
You ever think about having kids,
being a papa yourself?
♪♪
Once maybe.
[CHUCKLES]
My Margarethe,
she's... enough for me.
She's my heart.
This is the longest I've
ever been away from her.
26 years,
never this long away from home.
♪♪
To home.
Yeah.
[GLASSES CLINK]
♪♪
MAN: Hey, Mike.
I've got check on the boys.
You gonna be all right here?
Of course. I'll be fine. Go.
[BILLIARD BALLS CLACKING]
♪♪
- [HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYS IN CLUB]
- NICK: Sorry, Mike.
This guy slipped off
for a private dance.
You're not throwing me
out. I paid my money.
You paid to look, not touch, asshole.
That's it. I'm calling the cops.
Let's see how you like
hanging out in MDC.
No, no, no, no. You don't
need to call the cops.
Who the hell are you?
I'm the guy who's telling
you this one's had too much,
and I'm here to get
him out of your hair.
What about his buddies?
They're not causing
any trouble, are they?
Let them stay awhile longer.
This one...
this idiot goes home, sleeps it off.
No, no. I'm not going. I paid...
You... are done.
♪♪
Go on. Try me.
[CHUCKLES]
Get him out of here.
♪♪
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Sorry.
♪♪
The girl... is she okay?
She's fine. Seen worse.
This is for her trouble.
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
All good?
Yeah, man. We're cool.
♪♪
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYS,
INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
So... like this.
How about... [SIGHS]
♪♪
Nein. Nein, nein, nein, nein.
Terry, support must be invisible.
You can't throw a column
here, a column there.
Maximum volume and open space inside.
The final structure
has strict requirements.
Load-bearing walls, then.
Very good! [LAUGHS]
Now you use your thinking
head, not your drinking head!
But how do you get walls in place?
There would be seven,
eight meters to a side.
Pre-pour them off site.
Slide the slabs in with the crane.
Slide?
- Through the existing construction?
- [DOOR CLOSES]
You would knock down
the Chrysler Building
just to add a subway stop, huh?
No! The... Ah.
Time to go, yeah?
Mike, come sit with us.
Your wife's calling.
My wife?
Yeah.
♪♪
Ah. Okay. [CHUCKLES]
Thank you very much,
gentlemen, for your hospitality.
Good talking to you, Werner.
Auf Wiedersehen.
♪♪
[ENGINE REVS IN DISTANCE]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[SIGHS]
[IGNITION CLICKS]
[ENGINE STARTS, HEADLIGHT SWITCH CLICKS]
[GEARSHIFT CLICKS]
[ENGINE REVS]
[GRAVEL CRUNCHES]
♪ Boiling but not overflowing ♪
♪ Fails to only make
a better comeback ♪
♪ More powerful and
poignant and falls again ♪
♪ Destructive lust
for life erected ♪
- ♪ On the verge pricked up, like a picket ♪
- [SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
♪ Fearing to respond to the tempting ♪
Oh, hey. You say something?
- [MUSIC CONTINUES IN HEADPHONES]
- Yeah. I'm gonna head over
to the nail salon, finish setting up.
Oh. That's a good idea.
I'll see you later.
♪♪
♪ Dum, da de dum, da de dum ♪
♪ Da de, da da, de dum ♪
♪ Da de dum, da de dum ♪
♪ Da de, da da ♪
♪♪
Yeah. I won't be that long.
Uh, you want me to bring you something,
maybe Flying Star or... ?
Oh, no. I'm just gonna scrounge here.
I think we have some old Chinese.
But pick something
up for yourself, 'Kay?
Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
All right.
[SIGHS]
[MUSIC PLAYS INDISTINCTLY IN HEADPHONES]
♪♪
[AQUARIUM BUBBLING]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[JIMMY SIGHS]
[PAPER RUSTLES]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[SNIFFS, SIGHS]
Leaving now. You stick around?
Oh, uh, yeah.
I, uh... I'll be here a little longer.
I'll lock up when I
go. Is that all right?
Wife mad at you?
She's not my wi...
[SIGHS]
I don't know.
Yeah.
She's mad at you.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[SIGHS]
[METAL CLINKS]
[SNIFFS]
[BOTTLE THUDS]
Go on.
[DOOR CREAKS]
- [EXHALES SHARPLY]
- You take her to dinner...
nice place with a waiter, cloth napkin.
You bring flowers.
You say sorry.
Then say sorry again.
Whatever she says, you say sorry.
I think we might be past that.
I'll leave the bottle.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[CUP THUDS LIGHTLY]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[SIGHS]
[MACHINE WHIRS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Are you ready for me?
I'm a little early.
No problem. Come on in.
This is Gary Strote, Stef Carvaines,
and Pat Malakovsky, my associates.
- Hi.
- Suzanne Ericsen.
- Hello.
- Good to meet you all.
Nice to meet you.
[PAPERS THUD]
[BRIEFCASE CLOSES]
All right. You have a
response to our proffer?
We do.
Time served, three to
six months probation,
we plead to simple battery.
- A misdemeanor.
- Yes.
You're asking to go from 18
months jail time down to nothing?
Sorry. I can't do that.
Okay.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
This is a motion for continuance.
We're gonna need more time
to prepare our defense.
The officer's report states
that he didn't canvass
- for additional witnesses...
- There were none.
And no one is contesting
that Mr. Babineaux struck the officer.
Be that as it may, there
are several businesses
nearby with security cameras.
We need time to subpoena all of them.
Isn't that a bit much?
We don't believe the
judge will see it that way.
We'd simply like to have the most
complete information at our disposal.
To that end, we're filing a
motion to compel discovery.
You want to open Officer
Platt's personnel file.
Good luck with that.
It's a reasonable Brady disclosure.
Officer Platt had a
history with Mr. Babineaux,
and we'd like to know its extent.
PAT: And if there's any larger
history Officer Platt has
with friends, relatives, or
colleagues of Mr. Babineaux,
we'd like to know that, too.
You're thinking of
pursuing civil litigation.
We are in conversation with the ACLU,
assessing the possibility that
Mr. Babineaux's civil rights
may have been violated.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Okay. Is that all?
For now.
[SMACKS LIPS] We will deal with
all of these issues in turn,
and then we will set a trial date.
I think that's all
we have to talk about.
All right, then.
Ms. Wexler, a word in private?
I'll catch up.
[DOOR OPENS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Kim, you're throwing three $400-an-hour
associates at a pro bono case?
I never said this was pro bono.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
Okay, what's the plan here, Kim?
Because shock and awe
isn't gonna cut it.
Bring every fancy associate you got,
file all the motions you want,
and at the end of all this,
your client is still going away.
Okay.
I guess we'll see.
[BRIEFCASE CLACKS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS,
TELEPHONES RINGING]
[INHALES SHAKILY]
[METAL DOOR CLANGING]
[CONVERSATIONS IN GERMAN]
Ah!
[CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE]
Everyone seems much improved.
This, uh, R and R was
a good idea, Michael.
[CHUCKLES]
I... is something the matter?
[CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE]
[LAUGHTER]
This?
[CHUCKLES]
Don't be concerned.
I said nothing.
Men at a bar talking to make talk.
And look... no details, no scale at all.
Could be a skyscraper,
could be a box for shoes.
[LIGHTS HUMMING]
[CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE]
I said nothing about the construction
that would not be true
for thousands of others.
By now, they have forgotten me entirely.
They forgot the German national
in the middle of Albuquerque
talking about pouring
hundreds of tons of concrete
at a secret underground location?
Yeah, you're right.
I'm sorry, Michael. I had too much beer.
And I may have said
more than I should have.
Listen to me carefully.
The man we're working
for is very serious.
Think about the precautions we take
to keep everything
that goes on here quiet.
Think about how much
money you're making.
Think about what happens
if something goes wrong.
Do you understand what
I am saying to you?
I do understand.
And I'm sorry to cause any problem.
You have my word...
nothing like this will happen again.
[CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE]
Okay.
Let's get you to work.
[CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE]
I have one question
for you, Ms. Ericsen.
- Are you prosecuting Santa Claus?
- Your Honor?
Because it looks like
"Miracle on 34th Street" in here.
This... this is just today,
today's batch, huh?
All addressed to me,
all from some backwater in Louisiana.
I... Look at... Uh,
"Get your hands off our hero," they say.
Uh, "Mercy for Huell
Babineaux," they say,
what... like I'm sending
him to the electric chair.
Come... Tell me, uh, Ms. Wexler,
did you start this
particular ball rolling?
Did I instruct the people
of Coushatta, Louisiana,
to start writing letters to the court?
No, Your Honor, I did not.
That being said, it's
clear Mr. Babineaux
has touched the lives of
many people in his hometown.
And I do know they're planning
to send a contingent here
to show their support during the trial.
Are you talking about a bunch
of yahoos packing my court?
I'm sorry, Your Honor,
but I'm not sure what bearing
any of this has on the case.
What does Mr. Babineaux's relationship
to his hometown in...
Did you say Louisiana?
Your Honor, this can't
be a complete surprise
to the Assistant District Attorney.
She knows the defendant's
history as well as I do.
Lookit, if I receive one more letter
from some
swamp-dwelling do-gooder,
- I'm gonna scream.
- Thank you for bringing
this situation to our
attention, Your Honor.
May I see one of these?
Oh, oh, take as many as you want.
Yeah, please, just take them all.
I have looked at this case.
It does not merit a circus.
Now, you two work it out!
- We've tried, Your Honor.
- Try again.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Pull the Babineaux file...
every parking ticket,
every time he is
mentioned in the records.
You... call the arresting officer
and find out what, if anything,
he left out of his reports.
I want known associates,
places of residence,
MVD records, all of it.
We missed something,
and I want to know what.
- [BIN THUDS]
- Right now! Go!
[TELEPHONES RINGING]
Ben!
Who we looking for?
I want to figure out
why a pickpocket has
people this overheated.
[BAG RUSTLING]
[PAPER TEARING]
[TELEPHONE RINGING,
INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
"Huell Babineaux is wrongfully accused.
He's a good man.
He'd never do nothing like
the things you say he's done.
He's a kind man and a
good friend to everyone."
Jesus. They do make him
sound like Santa Claus.
This one has a phone number.
Let me see this.
[DIAL TONE, KEYPAD BEEPING]
[LINE RINGING]
You've reached Elmer Fontaneau.
I'm not here at the moment,
but leave a message,
I'll get back to you as soon as I can.
- Have a blessed day.
- [ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS]
Hello, Mr. Fontaneau.
My name is Suzanne Ericsen
from the Albuquerque
District Attorney's office.
Um, could you give me a
call when you have a moment?
It's in regards to Huell Babineaux.
My number is 505-186-1945. Thanks.
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
[TELEPHONES RINGING]
[PAPER RUSTLING, RIPPING]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[LINE RINGING]
WOMAN: Hello?
Is this Eloise Luckard?
- Speaking.
- Hi, Ms. Luckard.
My name is Suzanne Ericsen.
I'm an Assistant District Attorney
in Albuquerque, New Mexico.
You wrote a letter to Judge Munsinger
about a Huell Babineaux.
Oh, I love Huell.
He's the dearest, dearest man.
[CHUCKLES] Um, do you mind my asking...
how exactly do you know Huell?
Oh, everyone in Coushatta knows Huell.
He's a pillar of our church.
And which church is that?
Free Will Baptist,
right over on Bogan Lane.
Um, I've seen several letters
from fellow members
of your congregation.
Could you explain to
me... is there some reason
why Huell in particular holds
so much esteem in your church?
- _
- I... I'm sorry.
Who... who are you again?
I'm... Um, I'm an
Assistant District Attorney
from Albuquerque, New Mexico.
I'm handling a case that
Mr. Babineaux's involved in.
Handling how?
ERICSEN: Um... I'm prosecuting it.
Y... you're the one persecuting our Huell?
H... how could you, to go after someone
so sweet and kind with all those lies?
Well, I'd tell you what
I really think of you,
but Jesus is listening, so
I'll just say... shame on you!
- I...
- [DIAL TONE]
Okay.
[BUTTON CLICKS]
All right.
Yeah, not too shabby.
I've been taking improv classes.
[TELEPHONES RINGING, PAPER RUSTLING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
- [CELLPHONE RINGING]
- Oh, shit. Which one is it?
- I... it's that one.
- Oh.
It's the church. The church, the church.
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry.
[PLASTIC RUSTLES]
[RINGING CONTINUES]
[BUTTON CLICKS, ORGAN MUSIC
PLAYS LOUDLY ON SPEAKERS]
[LOUISIANA ACCENT] Hello dere!
Free Will Baptist.
Pastor Hansford speaking.
Uh, who this?
Good afternoon, Pastor.
My name is Suzanne Ericsen.
I'm an Assistant District Attorney
from Albuquerque, New Mexico.
Ooh, that's a long way off, Cher!
Uh, can you hold on a second?
Uh, Clarence is going at the organ.
Just... [FINGERS SNAP]
I'm gonna step into the vestibule.
- [SPEAKER VOLUME DECREASES]
- Ah, there we go.
Uh, now, uh, what can I do for you,
Ms., uh... Ms. Ericsen, you say?
Mm-hmm.
Um, the court has received
numerous letters from
members of your congregation
in regards to Mr. Huell Babineaux.
May I ask you a couple of
questions about Mr. Babineaux?
[CLICKS TONGUE] Surely.
Uh, what I can tell you about our Huell?
Well, what kind of person
would you say Mr. Babineaux is?
Why, I'd say he's a lovely
person both inside and out.
Yes, I'm... I'm sure you'd say that
about all your parishioners.
[CHUCKLING] Well, I suppose I would.
But, no, no, Huell... Huell's special.
He's got a heart as big
as Lake Pontchartrain.
Mm.
Um, do you mind my asking...
what did he do to gain so
much devotion in Coushatta?
Well, ma'am, for starters,
he is a bona fide hero.
- He's a hero?
- Yes, ma'am.
See, about a year ago, there
was a fire in the rectory,
and it was during Bible
study, uh, at night
'cause, uh, some of the
old folks around here,
uh, they like to brush up on the Bible
before, uh, they go to slep,
you know, get right in
case the Lord call 'em home.
Mm. Yes.
And wouldn'tcha know it...
there was a short circuit
in the old coffee maker.
The whole thing catch fire,
and the flame leaped
up to the windowsill.
Well, Huell happened to
be visiting his people,
and he saw the smoke.
Well, what did he do?
He burst right in. [CHUCKLES]
And he carried out every
last one of them oldsters.
Mm, my goodness.
And, um, what happened to the church?
[CHUCKLING] The church is fine.
[FINGERS SNAP]
[KEYS CLACKING]
- I shudder to think...
- [COMPUTER DINGS]
... what might've happened
if God in His grace
hadn't seen fit to send us old Huell.
I see.
Now, y'all sound like a real nice lady,
and I know you're only doing your job,
but I want you to understand something.
I think you got the wrong
end of the stick here.
Huell Babineaux is very important to us.
Now, he...
[SIGHS] He... he would
never hurt a police officer.
I believe it's just a misunderstanding.
And I... I believe he might
have been helping his friend,
and... and that's the Huell that I know.
Well, well... Put that down, Clarence!
Get rid of them robes,
now! That's for communion!
Now... now, I will
be with you presently!
Uh, ma'am, is there anything
else I can help you with?
No. No, Pastor.
Thank you for your time.
I... I think that's all.
Oh, um, uh, have you set a
date yet for Huell's trial?
Uh, no, not yet.
Well, would you do me a kindness
and, um, ring me up when you do?
Because we got a
couple of charter buses.
We're gonna bring the whole congregation
up to y'all in Albuquerque.
[SMACKS LIPS] I'll make
sure to let you know.
Bless you.
And I look forward Ta meetin' ya.
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
[CHUCKLES]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS,
TELEPHONES RINGING]
[SIGHS]
Is it over?
[NORMAL VOICE] All right,
here's what we're gonna do.
I'm gonna take the church phone with me.
She might call back.
If any of these ring,
I want you to pick up
every third caller, okay?
30 seconds, max.
Stick to the script.
Let the rest go to voicemail.
- Uh...
- [DOOR OPENS]
... so, are we just supposed
to hang around here till...
You're paid for the day.
You stay until I say you can go.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
JIMMY: [SIGHS]
- [DOOR SLAMS]
- Well?
[EXHALES SLOWLY]
[MOANS LIGHTLY]
[CHUCKLES]
KIM: Do it one more time?
JIMMY: Are you sure you can take it?
I can if you can.
All right. You asked for it.
[LOUISIANA ACCENT] Hello dere!
Look in your heart, Cher,
and find forgiveness.
Let us take you on a
trip down N'awlins way,
where they put a little extra
roux in da gumbo. [CHUCKLES]
Whoo!
That's a beautiful red snapper.
It's wondermous. I guarantee!
Wow, it's just... it's
like I'm in the bayou.
Yes, well, I got crawdads in my pants.
[LAUGHS]
That's... that's not a thing.
- That's not a...
- It's a thing that happens to you
when you're... sitting in the bayou.
[LAUGHS]
The phones were genius.
- [NORMAL VOICE] The phones.
- Yeah.
Well, the phones were a touch.
This was all you, start to finish.
Bank shot off the judge.
Four months probation, time served.
It's like watching Roy Hobbs
smash out stadium lights.
Oh, yeah, but the D.A.
overplayed her hand.
- [CHUCKLING] No.
- Yeah.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[SIGHS]
- Got to go?
- Yeah.
What are you up to today?
[INHALES SHARPLY]
I'm, uh, gonna check
out an office on Lomas,
down by the courthouse.
I thought you already found one.
That one was, uh...
It was a little more
office than I needed.
Oh.
[SIGHS]
You working late?
Mm-hmm.
Playing catch-up.
[SIGHS]
All right.
I better go.
I got to go. I got to go. I need to go.
[SIGHS]
[SMOOCHES]
[SNIFFS]
[SWITCH CLICKS]
[SHOWER CURTAIN CLINKS]
[FAUCET TURNS ON, WATER RUNNING]
PAIGE: The near-term window is set,
but we have to hit every target
to stick to that time table.
As we look down the road,
we get more flexibility.
When we get to rollouts
in a 6-to-12-month timeline and beyond,
we have some breathing room.
It's an opportunity to retrench
and meet our minimum
capital requirements.
We should be stable as a table
by the time we start on Wyoming.
Sounds good.
We should talk about Wyoming.
Six months is gonna go by fast.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Unless...
- Kevin, did you have something?
- KEVIN: Oh, no, I'm sorry.
I don't want to slow us down.
And Paige will hate me
for bringing this up.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
What's on your mind?
Well, the foot traffic at
Tucumcari is off the charts,
and that's driving a
lot of new accounts.
Seems to me it's because the
building itself is damn eye-catching.
Now, I want to hit on
all the milestones we're talking about.
And Paige tells me what I'm gonna
ask is impossible, but, uh...
what if we made the Lubbock
branch the same as Tucumcari?
I reminded Kevin that Tucumcari
has a much larger footprint
than the current Lubbock design,
and that design is the one
- we've been hanging our estimates on.
- I know. I know.
We're down the road a
ways on this, but, uh...
what do you think, Kim?
Can you pull another rabbit
out of the hat for us?
[CHUCKLES]
Kevin, I'm sorry.
But I have to agree with Paige.
It took almost two months
to get local approval
for the current design,
so starting over now?
There's simply no way we
could stick to our timetable.
I hate to say it, but...
it is. It's unfeasible.
Okay.
I get it. I had to ask.
Paige, you were right.
This time.
All right. Wyoming, then.
Yellowstone, here we come.
PAIGE: Great.
So, looking to Wyoming,
we are moving forward with
market research as planned.
♪♪
[METAL CLINKS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS
TELEPHONES RINGING]
♪♪
MIKE: Space is closing in
on rough final dimensions.
Most of the spoil's out and dispersed.
The tunnel is holding, and it's clear.
- And the front loader...
- [FLASHLIGHT CLICKS]
... hit this support stanchion.
The guys had it back up in an hour.
No permanent damage.
And the form they used
to pour cement into...
it's totaled.
We're gonna have to make a new one
before we can get back to the wall.
So we're looking at four,
maybe five days for that.
Coulda been worse.
The rock... that is more of an issue.
It is smack dab in the
middle of our elevator shaft.
Can't work around it, can't dig it out.
So we're back to blasting.
Setup, clearing away debris
adds maybe another week.
The best estimate...
we're a little past the halfway point.
Way behind schedule.
But the work is solid.
And Werner?
[SIGHS]
I gave him the "come to Jesus."
He screwed up.
He knows it, said it won't happen again.
And what do you say?
I've got eyes on him.
But, yeah, he's good.
Good.
[WATER DRIPPING]
Is that water?
AGENT: The landlord will kick
in for small repairs like that.
They already took care
of the rodent problem.
Rodent problem?
You asked for small and near court.
This is both.
And it's in your price range.
Use your imagination.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Think creatively.
Uh, excuse me for a sec, would you?
Yeah. Take your time.
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
JIMMY: Hey.
KIM: Hey.
Is this your new office?
Uh, it's a contender.
What are you doin' here?
I was driving, saw your
Esteem in the parking lot.
So, what's up?
Nothing.
Just drivin' around,
thinking about things.
Listen, Kim, I... I
know what's on your mind.
The thing that we did...
I mean, it was nuts.
[SIGHS]
And I dumped it in your lap.
Ex parte communication,
contempt of court.
I mean, what, we're talking about
a couple hundred counts of mail fraud?
I could have wrecked
you with Schweikart.
Could bone me, too.
I mean, I'm this close
to being reinstated.
I mean, come on.
[SIGHS]
Kim...
don't worry.
No one's gonna know about it.
Be like it never happened.
And also I agree...
we are totally done with all that,
over and out, no more.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Let's do it again.
[VEHICLE PASSING]
[HORN HONKS]
[LOS IMPERIALS "AL COMPAS
DE MI CABALLO" PLAYING]
♪♪
♪ Por el camino real por donde ♪
♪ Paso en mi cabello ♪
♪ Con mi mochila en el hombro,
y mi machete terciado ♪
♪ Y mi sombrero para
un hombre enamorado ♪
♪ Paca paca paca en mi caballo ♪
♪♪
NACHO: ♪ Paca paca
paca en mi caballo ♪
♪ Paca paca paca en mi caballo ♪
♪♪
[FOOD SIZZLING]
♪ Mi caballo es el mejor por su ♪
♪ Paso moderado ♪
Oh! Hey!
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
Hold on one second. Wait.
You are going to love this.
I made this just for you.
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
_
♪♪
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
♪ En mi caballo ♪
_
[SNIFFS]
I used epazote. Now, come on.
♪ Paca paca paca en mi caballo ♪
_
♪♪
- The Salamanca family.
- Them!
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
But you can call me Lalo.
[CHUCKLES]
_
[SINGING IN SPANISH]
What are you doing here?
Ah, I'm just here to
lend a helping hand,
you know, make sure the
business is running in order.
I got a... I got a
good head for numbers.
But listen... don't even worry.
It's gonna be like I'm not even here.
♪♪
♪ Paca paca paca en mi caballo ♪
NACHO: [SPEAKING SPANISH] _
♪ Paca paca paca ♪
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -