Previously on "Better Call Saul"...
Welcome to the team.
I'm not taking the job! Suckers.
She's proven she can field
whatever we throw at her
and then some.
I promised you Mesa Verde
would be my sole focus, and I meant it.
Oh, what's this?!
One last "Screw you, little brother"
from beyond the grave?!
JIMMY: I got something for you.
It's a job.
I think you're really gonna like this.
From now on, you are mine.
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
[CHAIN SCRAPING AND RATTLING]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES, ENGINE STARTS]
[ENGINE RUMBLING]
[ENGINE REVS, TIRES SQUEAL]
[TIRES POP, AIR HISSES]
[METAL SCREECHING]
[TIRE RIMS CLANG]
[RUBBER FLAPPING]
[SCREECHING CONTINUES]
[BRAKES SCREECH LIGHTLY,
ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
[HISSING, CRACKLING]
[BIRD CAWS]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[ENGINE RUMBLING]
[GLASS AND METAL CLATTERING]
[GEARSHIFT CLICKS]
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
[BIRD CHIRPING]
[VEHICLE DOOR OPENS]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[TRUNK LID CREAKS]
[GUN COCKS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
[SHELL CASINGS CLATTERING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[GUN CLICKS]
[MAGAZINE CLICKS]
[MAGAZINE CLATTERS, GUNSHOTS CONTINUE]
[GUNSHOTS CONTINUE]
[CASING CLATTERS]
[GLASS CRUNCHES]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
[BLOOD SPLATTERS]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[BIRD CAWS]
[GLASS CLATTERS, CRUNCHES]
[CARD DOOR CREAKS, CLOSES]
[CHIRPING CONTINUES]
[GUN CLICKS]
Aah!
[CASING CLATTERS]
[CHIRPING CONTINUES]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[GRAVEL CRUNCHING]
[GROANS LIGHTLY]
[GLASS RATTLES, DOOR CREAKS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Can I make the call now?
[FLESH TEARS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
NACHO: [GROANS]
Gotta make it look real.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[BLOOD DRIPPING]
[BREATHING RAGGEDLY]
Do it quick before you pass out.
[GASPING]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
- [DIALING]
- [BREATHES DEEPLY]
♪♪
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
[FIGURINE CLACKS,
INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[MID-TEMPO COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYS ON STEREO]
And?
What if I told you, you could turn
this piece of crap into four grand
for each of us, minimum?
This little fella...
he's called the Merry Wanderer.
He's not much to look at.
He's pretty easy to find.
I got this one at a pawn shop
on 4th for 20 bucks.
But he has a cousin called Bavarian Boy,
almost identical...
same umbrella, same swagger.
That one is worth a boatload.
And I gather you know
where to find a Bavarian Boy.
I do, indeed.
He's gathering dust on a shelf
in an office up on San Mateo,
and he's been there
for God knows how long.
And they have no idea what they've got.
To them, it's not Bavarian Boy.
It's just "some piece of junk
grandma gave me
that I feel too guilty to get rid of."
And that's where you come in.
- [BELL DINGS]
- Now, this place I'm talking about...
they're not exactly what
you call security-conscious.
There's no cameras whatsoever.
There's an alarm on the door
that I could probably bridge.
And past that, you just pick a lock
and walk over to the shelf
and swap this Wanderer for that Boy,
and it's five minutes, max.
Warm-up, gentlemen?
Yeah. Thanks, Fran.
- Oh, thanks.
- [CHUCKLES]
That's cute.
- Isn't it, though?
- Yeah.
Have your food up in a jiff, Mike.
- Mm.
- [SIGHS]
Look, they're not even
gonna know it's gone.
They look over at the shelf,
they just see
the same dumb tchotchkes staring at them
they've been looking at for years.
There's no serial number.
These things are practically untraceable.
Now, you send Pryce or some other schlub
down to Dallas next week.
They're having a collectibles expo.
Those people are hungry for Hummels.
I mean, their eyes are gonna pop
when they see what we brung 'em.
And they will pay through the nose,
which we will split fifty-fifty.
So, it's perfect, right?
We make some nice
Hummel-loving lady happy,
and we make a bundle.
Let's do something beautiful here.
And how did you come across
this valuable wunderkind?
What difference does it make?
Guys in the office cross you?
Done you wrong?
[EXHALES SHARPLY] What?
[CHUCKLES]
You're, uh, missing the point.
It's free money.
You walk by a $20 on the sidewalk?
No. You pick it up.
[MID-TEMPO PIANO MUSIC PLAYS ON STEREO]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Pass.
What? Why?
It's not for me.
Not for you?
Is there some problem I'm not seeing,
like with the swap or something?
Plan's fine, as far as it goes.
It's just not for me.
And I don't think
it should be for you, either.
[BELL DINGS]
I'm sorry about your brother.
Yeah. Thanks.
But you're really not gonna do this?
Sorry.
[CASH REGISTER DINGS]
- Eggs easy.
- MIKE: Thanks, Fran.
Can I get you anything else?
No. I'm good.
Sure I can't get you anything?
No. I'm not hungry. Thanks.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
- All right.
- [KEYS CLACK]
I, um...
[SILVERWARE CLANKING]
If you don't want easy money,
that's your business.
I just thought I'd give you first crack
at a golden opportunity.
All right. We'll see you around.
[UTENSILS CLACKING]
You take it easy.
- [DOOR OPENS]
- [INHALES DEEPLY]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Yes. Hello.
I was wondering if Dr. Caldera
had any openings today.
As soon as possible.
I have a very sick fish.
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
♪♪
[METAL CLANKING]
[TRUNK LID CREAKS]
♪♪
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Ah.
- Thanks.
- [ELEVATOR DINGS]
And, uh, thanks again for the lift.
It's outside your
job description, I know.
VIOLA: It's no problem.
So, the acquisitions?
Yes. We'll need to draft
contracts for the target banks.
The idea is to have
the agreements ready to go
while we're doing due diligence.
You want me to start cracking on
a draft when we're done here?
- [TELEPHONE RINGING]
- No. But thank you.
I'll do the first pass,
and then you can proof it.
- [ELEVATOR DINGS, DOORS OPEN]
- Sure. Whatever's best for you.
[CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE]
KIM: Here's what I'm thinking.
Looking at the competition,
one opportunity stands out.
They don't have the market share, but...
and this is a big deal...
Walker Ridge is eager.
I agree.
They took a hit in the market adjustment.
They're vulnerable, and they know it.
I think we should prepare
a package for both
- with that in mind...
- [DOOR OPENS]
Is that Kim Wexler I hear?
Kevin.
It's good to see you.
I heard you were here,
just wanted to say hi.
Look at you.
Baby bird with a broken wing.
Oh, it's fine. It doesn't even hurt.
Just a pain in the butt.
Kevin, this is Viola Goto,
my new paralegal.
Viola. Kevin Wachtell.
Welcome to the team.
Nice to meet you.
Listen, Kim, I just wanted to say
how sorry I am about Charles McGill.
It's no secret
I had problems with the man,
but, uh, no one should go like that.
You know, I just have to ask...
how's James handling it?
- Oh, he's...
- he's getting through it.
He and the family really appreciated
the arrangement you sent for the funeral.
Good. Well, glad to hear it.
Uh, Kevin, you remember
we're meeting the board at noon
to go over Kim's recommendations, so...
No, no, no, I won't slow you down.
Oh, uh, one more thing...
and this will just take a second...
Kim, you have got to see the models.
The... models?
[LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS]
Takes your breath away, doesn't it?
[CHUCKLES]
Look at this.
The whole side of this building is glass,
and it's on a north-facing lot.
I'm told that's energy-efficient,
so I'm excited about that.
This is, uh, Salt Lake City?
After Provo, why not?
[SMACKS LIPS] And...
- Cheyenne, Wyoming?
- Yep.
Over here, North Platte, Nebraska.
Now, these two you already know.
This one's gonna be Ogden, Utah,
and this one here is Tucumcari.
And over here on this side,
you got a few new ones... Sedona,
Pueblo, Colorado.
And you know what? That's
just the tip of the iceberg.
After that, I figure why not Las Vegas?
Nevada, I mean. Reno, too.
Lubbock, Texas, Amarillo,
San Antonio, El Paso.
Then we're gonna get up
to the Pacific Northwest...
Boise, Bend, Oregon,
Eugene, Salem,
all the way up to Portland.
KEVIN: Now, this one
is real special... Denver.
See here?
We're gonna go ahead and add
more trees on the west side,
and that'll be great, and then maybe a...
a bench or two on the outside.
Kim, is there something wrong?
No. No. No, no.
No. It's just... It's a lot.
It's a very fast, aggressive expansion.
Kevin figures once we get
our foothold in Utah,
then we'll file for federal charter.
Yeah.
We're really building something here.
All your hard work
is making a difference.
I mean, Kim, this is what it's all about.
So, I can get the notes to you
by EOD, if that's okay.
Uh, yeah, that's fine.
Do you have a sense
when I should expect your draft?
I assume you're dictating it.
[WATER RUSHING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Actually, you were right before.
Why don't you take a stab at it,
and then I'll take a look?
Great. That works.
I'll start on that
right after I get you home.
Uh, instead of taking me home,
drop me off at the courthouse, would you?
Oh, I didn't realize
you had an appearance today.
- I would have prepped.
- No. No, I don't.
- You don't?
- Nothing to prep.
Don't worry about it.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
- [DOGS BARKING]
- Yeah. No.
- [TELEPHONE RINGING]
- [JIMMY SIGHS]
No.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
No, not the dog.
I-I've done business
with him before, yeah.
Once. Once.
[KNOCK ON WINDOW]
Just the once.
Yeah.
[SIGHS]
I guess. I don't know.
CALDERA: He didn't say.
- Well?
Yeah. He's not into it.
He's not into it, or you're not into it?
- Give me that.
- Unh-unh.
It doesn't work that way.
No direct contact. That's the point.
Just give it to me.
[SIGHS]
- Take it.
Hey. This is the interested party.
I have one question for you.
Do you shit gold?
Well, it's a simple yes or no.
No. All right, then.
Because unless you currently have
a large gold nugget
traversing your colon,
this is the easiest money
you're ever gonna make.
How long does it take for you
to pick a Yale three-pin?
Well, then in 8 minutes,
you're gonna make 4 grand,
10 minutes if you decide
to pick your nose.
In, out, no one comes
looking for you ever.
How does that sound?
Yeah, I know where that is.
Here. [SNAPS FINGERS] Pen.
Uh-huh.
In a half an hour.
- Yep.
- [CELLPHONE CLICKS]
See, I'm not trying to tell you
how to do your job, but...
[DOG BARKING]
WOMAN: All right, Mr. McGill,
you're all set.
All right. Thank you very much.
See ya next time.
- I hope she feels better soon.
- [TELEPHONE RINGING]
[DOOR CREAKS]
Excuse me.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[DOGS BARKING]
Can... I help you?
♪♪
Jesus.
[ SIGHS ] Uh, not here.
Let me go grab my bag and tell my staff.
[SIGHS] Jesus.
♪♪
- CALDERA: [SPITS]
- [SYRINGE CAP CLATTERS]
[GROANS]
[ENGINE RUMBLING]
[VEHICLE RATTLES]
[ECHOING, DISTORTED] Can you not
hit every damn pothole, please?!
♪♪
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[GROANING]
[ECHOING] Careful. Careful!
♪♪
Up, up.
[GROANING CONTINUES]
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
[CLAPS HANDS] [NORMAL VOICE]
You, ayuda. Come here.
Help.
♪♪
[LIQUID DRIPPING]
[SNIFFS]
♪♪
[SCISSORS SNIP]
[RUBBER GLOVES SNAPPING]
[GROANS]
[TONGUE CLICKS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
[LIQUID DRIPPING]
CALDERA: Well, well, there he is.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
You woke up.
That means my Spanish is good enough
and Yul Brynner over here
is actually O-negative.
Okay. [SIGHS]
I had to leave a bullet in your shoulder.
Might set off
metal detectors from now on.
Gave ya a dose
of broad-spectrum antibiotics.
Let's see.
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
Pulse is good.
Now, sniff test says you probably
didn't perforate your bowel... probably.
I can't be 100 percent sure
you didn't get nicked.
Now, if this starts to leak,
you're gonna get the worst
infection of your life.
It's gonna hurt like hell,
and then you're gonna die.
So I advise you
to go see a doctor
that has some imaging tech...
in other words, one that's not working
out of the back of a Jiffy Lube.
Till then,
keep these clean and dry,
change the bandages daily...
you should be okay.
You understand me?
[SNIFFS, SWALLOWS]
Good.
[WHISPERING] Now, understand this.
After I walk out of here,
I never want to see you again.
Never.
This cartel shit is too hot for me.
You got it? [INHALES DEEPLY]
[EXHALES SHAKILY]
[BAG SNAPS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[METAL SCRAPING]
[DEVICE CLICKS]
[LOCK RATTLING]
[LOCK DISENGAGES]
♪♪
[DOOR CLOSES]
[FLASHLIGHT CLICKS]
♪♪
[TOILET FLUSHES]
[SIGHS]
[LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS]
[EXHALING SHARPLY]
[CLOCK TICKING]
[SIGHS]
[DOORKNOB RATTLING]
[DOOR CREAKS, CLOSES]
[TICKING CONTINUES]
[SIGHS, COUGHS]
[EXHALING HEAVILY]
[TICKING CONTINUES]
[SIGHS]
[LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS]
[GLASS CLINKS]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS]
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
It's me.
Can we talk, please?
I-I just want to come home.
Okay. Thank you.
I-I just wanted to say
I'm sorry if you feel upset.
It was not my intention
f-for you to feel upset.
Well, m-my intention was for...
Honey, it is top-of-the-line.
[STAMMERS] Then what is the point?
You're saying I'm a...
I'm a thoughtless...
that I don't care,
but it is a very, very expensive vacuum.
[SCOFFS]
It... It never loses suction!
- [TELEPHONE THUDS]
- So, what you're saying
is I've got... I got to sleep
in my office
because I got you a gift?!
Lynette?
[HANDSET SLAMS]
[SIGHS] Damn it.
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
[DRAWER OPENS]
[DRAWER CLOSES]
[KEYPAD CLICKING]
[SNIFFS]
Hello. Are you still delivering?
Oh. Okay.
[SIGHS]
[TICKING CONTINUES]
Uh, yeah, just a large cheese.
Yes. Sliced, please.
Could you also throw in
some dipping sticks?
Two ranch and one marinara.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[SIGHS]
[CELLPHONE VIBRATING]
[DOOR CLOSES SOFTLY]
Hey. How'd it go?
- NEFF: Thank you.
- Listen. Listen.
- I was...
- Look. [SIGHS]
- The office guy... he's here.
[CHUCKLING] What?
He's dug in for the night, man.
- Thanks. You too.
- Come get me or... Come get me!
[DOOR CREAKS, CLOSES]
[SIGHS]
[CELLPHONE CLACKS]
MAN ON STEREO: Now, if you'll take
out the little listener's guide
that came with the program,
you'll see a chart in there
showing four quadrants
I call the Time Management Matrix.
The key words to understand
are "importance" and "urgency."
Importance basically comes
from within you.
Importance is your value system,
hopefully based on principles.
- [PEN SCRATCHING]
- Importance is your mission...
[MUFFLED] Importance...
- ...your central strategy...
- ...versus...
...to accomplish those
high-priority goals...
...urgency.
...and the plan to
implement that strategy.
- Urgency comes from the environment...
- [CAR ALARM BLARING, HORN HONKING]
...it presses upon you.
Its proximate is right in front of you.
And it's often very popular.
I could be deep and...
[STEREO TURNS OFF]
[BLARING, HONKING CONTINUE]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[KEYS JANGLING]
[LOCK DISENGAGES]
[GRUNTS]
[CAR ALARM CHIRPS,
BLARING AND HONKING STOPS]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[KEYS JANGLING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[LOCK ENGAGES]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[SIGHS]
♪♪
[SIGHS, CLICKS TONGUE] Son of a bitch.
[GRUNTS]
[METAL CLINKING]
♪♪
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[CAR ALARM BLARING, HORN HONKING]
[METAL RATTLING]
MAN ON STEREO: ...it's urgent,
- it has the appearance...
- Oh, God.
- ...of requiring immediate attention.
- [SIGHS]
Now, you have to decide what is
truly important in your life.
That's why I...
[BLARING, HONKING CONTINUE]
[KEYS JANGLING]
Hey. Hey!
- Hey!
- [LOCK DISENGAGES]
Hey!
Stop! Stop!
Oh, no! No!
Hey! No! No! Why? Why?
Stop! No, stop! Stop!
[PARKING BRAKE CLICKS, TIRES SCREECH]
- [SIGHS]
- [CAR ALARM CHIRPS, STOPS]
♪♪
Hey! Hey.
So, did you get it?
Shitting gold.
- Yeah. Yeah, right?
- [CHUCKLES]
I didn't say it was easy.
Car thing was pretty slick.
I don't know how you pulled that off.
Worked, though, didn't it?
Yeah. I guess so.
[CELLPHONE RINGS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Yes?
BOLSA: The Salamancas were hit.
Yesterday, on the way back
from their pickup.
GUS: Do we know who?
[SIGHS] Not yet.
Varga survived barely,
but he couldn't see faces.
- Someone knows our business.
- Possibly.
It resembled the attack
on Hector's truck a few months ago,
and they knew
the Salamanca men were heavy.
Don Juan, we are about to run
another shipment.
If you think we're compromised...
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Run dummy loads.
We'll see what we see.
No product crosses until we're certain.
I'll take care of it.
How long before our dealers run dry?
No more than a week.
[SIGHS]
This is a problem.
[MAN SPEAKING SPANISH]
Find a local supplier
on your side of the border.
Cut a deal.
Don Juan, with all due respect,
Don Eladio forbids buying from outsiders.
He's been very clear.
Let me worry about Eladio.
Do it now.
[MEN SPEAKING SPANISH]
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
[CELLPHONE CLACKS]
[SIGHS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE]
[AIR HISSES, DOOR CLOSES]
MAN: ♪ There's antimony,
arsenic, aluminum, selenium ♪
♪ And hydrogen and oxygen
and nitrogen and rhenium ♪
♪ And nickel, neodymium,
neptunium, germanium ♪
♪ And iron, americium,
ruthenium, uranium ♪
♪ Europium, zirconium,
lutetium, vanadium ♪
♪ And lanthanum and osmium
and astatine and radium ♪
♪ And gold and protactinium
and indium and gallium ♪
[INHALES DEEPLY] ♪ And iodine and
thorium and thulium and thallium ♪
♪ There's yttrium, ytterbium,
actinium, rubidium ♪
♪ And boron, gadolinium,
niobium, iridium ♪
♪ There's strontium and silicon
and silver and samarium ♪
♪ And bismuth, bromine, lithium,
beryllium, and barium ♪
[UP-TEMPO PIANO MUSIC PLAYING
IN HEADPHONES]
Oh. [CHUCKLES]
- Uh, Mr. Fring.
- [BUTTON CLICKS, MUSIC STOPS]
I wasn't expecting you.
That's not a problem, I hope.
No, not at all.
I was tinkering with something.
What's that?
Oh, it's, uh, technical.
I wouldn't want to bore you.
Oh, you wouldn't.
Okay.
You know when you put salt
into water, it dissolves?
If you stir the water or heat it,
you can add more salt
than you could otherwise
before it falls out of solution.
I'm trying to create
a solution... like that,
but with certain benzodiazepine
precursor compounds.
[CLICKS TONGUE] That's fascinating.
It will be if I can get it to work.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Oh, I tested your samples.
[KEYS CLACK]
[LOCK DISENGAGES]
[DRAWER CLOSES]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
They range from 39 percent
to 58 percent pure,
except this one, which hovers around 67.
Top of the class, so to speak.
You should tell the chemist to check
his... or her... cookware.
It's introducing contamination,
which would be easy to avoid.
Well, thank you very much, Gale.
That's very useful information.
Well, I should let you
get back to your work.
Mr. Fring, um, I-I don't
want to cast aspersions,
but I have to tell you,
these samples aren't great.
I-In fact, they're, um...
they're... they're not even good.
Basically, they're dreck.
I could do much better...
- Gale...
- ...much higher-grade.
I could make a kilo or more right here,
and no one would know.
Wouldn't take more than a few days.
I wouldn't want to interfere
with your studies.
These are my studies.
Please. It's the least I can do.
I wouldn't let you down.
[CHUCKLING] Oh.
I'm certain that you wouldn't.
But I'm afraid I can't
allow it... not yet.
You were meant for better things.
I'll see you soon, Gale.
Bye, Mr. Fring.
[FOOTSTEPS DEPART]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CREAKS, CLOSES]
[TOM LEHRER'S "THE ELEMENTS"
PLAYS IN HEADPHONES]
♪ There's holmium and helium
and hafnium and erbium ♪
♪ And phosphorus and francium
and fluorine and terbium ♪
♪ And manganese and mercury,
molybdenum, magnesium, ♪
♪ Dysprosium and scandium
and cerium and cesium ♪
♪ And lead, praseodymium
and platinum, plutonium, ♪
♪ Palladium, promethium,
potassium, polonium ♪
♪ Tantalum, technetium,
titanium, tellurium ♪
[INHALES DEEPLY]
♪ And cadmium and calcium
and chromium and curium ♪
Oh, I was worried
about the wording there.
Hmm? No, no. It's great.
Oh.
Really, really solid work.
Just make the change
to indicate the correct term
for the disbursement of funds,
and then we should be good to go.
- Okay.
- [SIGHS]
Don't mind me. I know it's a law office.
I'm just walking around your law office.
You slept late.
Yeah.
It took me awhile
to fall asleep, actually,
but, man, once I did, I...
Uh, you want some coffee, Viola?
Oh, no, thanks. We're just finishing up.
Unless there's something else
you need from me.
No. I think we're good.
Maybe, uh, you could also start looking
into federal charter regs.
No rush.
- [CEREAL CLINKING]
- Got it. Will do.
Bye, Jimmy.
See ya, Viola.
Bye. Thanks.
[SIGHS]
[MILK POURING, SLOSHING]
[CEREAL RUSTLING]
[SPOON SCRAPES]
- [SIGHS]
- [CEREAL CRUNCHING]
JIMMY: [SNIFFS, SIGHS]
[CEREAL CRUNCHING]
What's up?
Jimmy, there's just a couple of things,
from talking to Howard, that...
[SNIFFS]
...maybe we ought to go through.
Oh, yeah. Okay.
Yeah, let's get it over with, you know?
Rip the Band-Aid off, right?
Yeah. Uh, this is a release.
It says basically that
you won't contest the will.
If I sign it, I get my share?
That's about the size of it.
So, uh [CLEARS THROAT] how much do I get?
$5,000.
[SCOFFS]
Five K.
Yeah.
[CHUCKLES]
I can pay off my Mastercard.
[PEN SCRATCHING]
[PEN CLICKS, CLATTERS]
- What else you got?
- [SIGHS]
- Um...
- [SPOON SCRAPES]
- ...this is...
- [SPOON CLANKS]
[SMACKS LIPS, SIGHS]
It's from Chuck.
Nobody knows for sure what's in it.
You don't have to open it
right now, but...
Let's see what the old boy has to say.
Okay, I'll... I'll give you
a minute alone.
No, no. Stay. It's fine.
I mean, uh, you want to hear this, right?
Yeah. If it's okay.
[SMACKS LIPS, SIGHS]
[SLURPS]
It's undated.
[SMACKS LIPS] Okay, here it goes.
[CLEARS THROAT] "Dear Jimmy,
I have left many things unsaid
in our relationship through the years.
Rather than all allow...
allow these unspoken thoughts
to die with me,
I've chosen to record them here for you.
I hope you will take my words
in the spirit in which
they are intended."
- [SPOON SCRAPES]
- [SMACKS LIPS, SIGHS]
[SPOON CLACKS]
[MUFFLED] New paragraph.
"I remember quite clearly
the day you came home from the hospital.
You can't imagine the joy on Mom's face.
I can honestly say
I never saw her happier
than she was on that day.
You brought a shine to her life
that nothing else ever did,
and I'm glad of that."
[SMACKS LIPS] New paragraph.
"We have not always seen eye to eye.
I expect that will continue
to be so in the future.
However, nothing will ever
change the fact
that we are brothers, flesh and blood.
And though we are very different people,
I want you to know how much I respect
what you have made of yourself
in these last few years.
You have taken the opportunity
I gave you in the mailroom,
and you have run with it,
becoming a valued member
of the HHM family.
For all the problems in your past,
I'm proud we share the name McGill."
- [SLURPS]
- [SPOON CLANKS]
"I sincerely admire
your energy and resilience.
I used to worry about you
finding a place in the world,
but I'm not worried about that anymore.
I'm certain now that, no matter
what the future may bring,
you'll land on your feet,
and I hope when you read this,
you remember me not only as your brother,
but as a person you knew
was always in your corner."
He signed it just "Chuck."
[PAPER THUDS]
- Well, say what you want,
the man could write a letter.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[Inhales deeply
- S-Sorry.
- Hey.
No, I didn't... I didn't
mean to make it...
No. It's okay.
It's okay. It's a nice letter.
- Hey.
- [VOICE BREAKING] No, just...
Just g... Just give me...
Just give me a minute.
[CRYING]
Kim.
[DOOR CREAKS]
[SIGHS]