Previously on "Better Call Saul"...
It was all you, start to finish.
Got to go.
Yep.
Perhaps we should
temper our expectations.
You can call me Lalo.
The Salamanca family.
It's gonna be like I'm not even here.
We're way behind schedule,
but the work is solid.
And Werner?
I've got eyes on him.
SAUL: The thing that we
did, I mean, it was nuts.
And I dumped it in your lap.
I'm this close to being reinstated.
Let's do it again.
[CRUTCHES CLUNKING]
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[COPY MACHINE WHIRRING]
Excuse me.
- May I help you?
- Oh, I really hope so.
What can I do for you?
Uh, my firm submitted
plans for Mesa Verde Bank.
We're building a branch here in Lubbock.
Oh, sure, I think I
saw that come through.
As I was cleaning up,
re-filing all our plans internally,
I realized I was missing
one of the old versions.
We had some late changes to
the conference-room dimensions,
so there were different
versions floating around
and things got really complicated.
Sorry. [CHUCKLES]
Whew.
So, long story short,
I think it's possible
the wrong version ended
up in our proposal.
- Oh, dear.
- Yeah.
So, I have the correct plans here,
and I was hoping to just take a look
at the approved plans to compare them,
- just to make sure.
- Okay. Okay.
Um, but if they're wrong,
you know you have to re-file...
Re-file. Yeah. I know. [CHUCKLES]
I just want to make sure they
actually are the wrong ones
before I, uh, get into it with my bosses.
No problem.
- Uh, Mesa Verde?
- Yes.
Do you have the address?
8783 Baylor Street.
I'll be right back.
Thank you.
[BRIEFCASE THUDS]
[SIGHS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
- [DOOR OPENS]
- SHIRLEY: Here we go.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Oh, I'll... I'll come around to you.
Oh, good. Thanks. [CHUCKLES]
Okay.
Yep. Dates match.
That's a good start. [CHUCKLES]
Uh, all right, conference
room is on sheet A1.1.
And room dimensions
should be 15'6 " by 12'6"?
Uh, 15'6 " by 12'6".
Great.
Uh, break or sprain?
- Huh?
- Uh, your foot.
Oh, uh, a sprain.
I started trail running
a couple months ago,
went for a run last week,
wasn't paying attention,
and got my foot snagged
in one of the roots,
- just twisted my ankle.
- Ohh.
Do you have a setback for
that conference-room wall
at 2 feet, 10 inches?
Uh, yes, the wall is set
back 2 feet, 10 inches.
So far, so good.
It hasn't been that bad except
I have an 8-month-old, so...
Oh, congratulations.
Thanks.
Been, you know, kind
of doing it on my own.
My brother's been helping
since I'm a little limited these days,
driving me around and whatnot.
Well, it's nice to have family around.
Yeah.
For the most part.
[CHUCKLES] He tries.
That's the important thing, right?
- [CHUCKLING] Oh. Yeah.
- Okay.
I think these are the same.
Am I missing anything?
They look the same to me.
- Great.
- [BOTH LAUGH]
- Yes!
- No re-filing.
Ahh. Thank you.
Uh, thank you, Shirley. God.
You're welcome.
You saved my life.
I am telling you, my bosses
would have murdered me.
I understand.
You know, you're the only
person in charge of organization,
- and suddenly everything's your fault, right?
- Mm-hmm.
I assume you would know all about that.
Yo, Lizzie.
Bill. Where's Aidan?
Oh. Hey, lady.
Um, he's fine, but he's very hungry.
- Bill. Bill...
- And he's like a little eating machine.
- Bill...
- Could you sniff this for me?
Bill! Where is Aidan?
He's fine. He's in the Wrangler.
- Just take a smell because...
- What?
- ...[SNIFFS] it's a little funky.
- You left my child in your Jeep?!
Yeah. I cracked the window, just...
- Bill...
- What?
- Check this...
- Just give me the keys.
- I'm not gonna check it!
- Where ya going?
To get Aidan because you
can't leave a baby in a car.
What the hell is wrong with you?!
Oh, man.
- Get... Go get the...
- What?
- Go get the baby, Bill.
- What did I do?
- Help her!
- Well, it's only been a minute.
- I didn't know!
- [KIM SIGHS]
Sorry. [SLURPING]
What am I supposed to do?
KIM: What are you supposed to do?
You're supposed to watch a
baby for five minutes in a car.
How hard is that?
Slow down. I'm wearing flip-flops.
[CRUTCHES CLUNKING]
How's Aidan?
Oh, he's fine.
He was only alone for
a minute, thank God.
Wait. What... What happened?
- Your milk...
- What?
Well, it... it just
kind of went everywhere.
- What are you talking...
- I am so sorry.
What... Oh, my God.
[GASPS] Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- I... I...
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
- Shirley, I can't! Shirley, that's not...
- A-All right, all right.
Oh, my God, they don't
even know I'm in Texas!
L-Listen, this is what we're gonna do.
This is what we're gonna do.
- [GASPING]
- You're gonna give me your copy,
and I'll trade them out.
W-Won't you get in trouble?
They're exactly the same.
No one has to know.
[EXHALES SHARPLY] Are you sure?
- Go on, Gettem.
- Okay.
Okay.
Okay, if you're sure.
Thank you so much.
Shirley...
I can't tell you how
much this means to me.
Really, you're a life-saver.
SHIRLEY: We need to stick together.
Being a mom is hard enough.
[CHUCKLES]
All right.
[SNIFFLES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
All right.
Let's make this official.
[STAMP MACHINE THUNKING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪ ♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
We have returned. Welcome
back to "The Newlywed Game."
Gentlemen, we've recorded
your predictions on cards.
You now have them flat on your laps.
Remember, each time
that your prediction
matches your wife's answer,
you get 5 points, and the one couple
with the most points
at the end of the show
wins a great second honeymoon.
So, ladies, we are so thrilled
that you did come back,
and here's your first
question for 5 points.
Tell me, ladies, if you were a boat,
does your husband think
you've been taking in the most
water lately on your stern...
on your port side, on your
starboard side, or on your bow?
Where you taking in that water, Laura?
- LAURA: My stern.
- [SPEAKING SPANISH] _
- On your stern.
- Definitely, yeah.
He said you've been taking a
lot of water in on your bow.
Bow?
MAN: The top half's the bow.
- Yeah, but...
- Okay.
I... I'm a little... Are
you saying I'm top-heavy?
- Lately.
- Lately? I guess. Okay.
Are you complaining?
- No, not at all.
- [LAUGHTER]
You don't like her
bow? I love her bow.
- [SPEAKING SPANISH] _
- I just thought my stern.
_
No. How's she stay afloat?
- [LAUGHTER]
- She's top-heavy.
- She's top-heavy?
- Yeah.
I see. Okay. Tammy, where
you taking in the water?
_
Oh, because your bow
is your stomach here.
Her bow is her top side.
Well, you know...
_
[CHUCKLES]
...said you've been taking
a lot of water in on your...
_
MAN: Big bow. [LAUGHS]
You don't like her stern?
_
[LAUGHS]
[LAUGHTER]
_
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION ON TV]
_
[CHUCKLES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
He said you dragged the telephone
and dropped if off a 10-story building.
[LAUGHS]
_
[CHUCKLES]
"Ding! Ding! Ding!" [LAUGHS]
_
...what will your husband say
you think he needs to work on
- before your next big match?
- [BELL DINGS]
_
- [CHUCKLES] _
- [BELL DINGING REPEATEDLY]
- [LAUGHING]
[DINGING CONTINUES]
[LAUGHING]
_
[LAUGHS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
I'm sorry he has a problem.
Laura?
LAURA: Definitely follow-through.
- Follow-through.
- Yeah.
Everything else is doing good,
but afterwards, he's
like, "Okay, what's next?
- Let's get up and go
- " Oh, really?
[LAUGHING] Yeah.
- That's 12:00 at night, right?
- Yeah...
Hey, why don't you, um,
go get some Jell-O?
WOMAN: Pacing, yeah. Everything
else is fine, just pacing.
We got a big pacing problem.
[CHUCKLES] Okay.
Next question, ladies...
How many gallons of water
will your husband say
the largest tub or sink
in your home holds?
_
[BELL DINGS]
I would say 32 maybe.
32. Wow. That's a guess, but...
- Yeah.
- [BELL DINGS]
...I'm not very good with,
like, measure stuff.
Laura?
LAURA: Probably smaller,
just, like, maybe 10.
- 10? 10 Gallons?
- 10. 10 gallons.
- Oh, my.
- Yeah. Smaller size.
- Pardon me?
- A smaller size.
He's not taking a bath, is he?
Well, we have a ver...
[SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
Same old Hector.
Just wants to kill everybody.
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
You know, the biggest pancake
is not the best pancake,
or they would call it
"the best pancake that
happens to be the biggest."
- [LAUGHS]
- Top off?
But, no, it's the... Thank you.
Can I get y'all anything else?
- Stuffed.
- Uh, we're good. Thanks.
[CHUCKLES] No, you don't
want a whole other burger?
Whenever you're ready. No rush.
Okay, thanks. [LAUGHS]
You better take it easy with that stuff.
Oh, we've still got at
least at hour on the road.
Gotta stay awake.
Yeah, but you got to be able
to sleep when we get home, too.
- What time is your hearing?
- 11:00.
This time next week,
I will once again be
James McGill, Esquire.
- Yes.
- Mm.
[WOMAN SINGING INDISTINCTLY]
Mm! And I already got a
jump on my new practice.
Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
[MUG THUDS]
Unexpected bonus of
the drop-phone business...
It turns out it's great
for client development.
Y-Yes, I-I guess that's true.
Sooner or later,
every last one of those idiots
is gonna need an attorney.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Of course, they all
know me as Saul Goodman.
- That's just details.
- [CHUCKLES]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
Got to say, a lot of people
are gonna be begging for the
old Huell Babineaux treatment.
And what's that?
Our powers...
combined.
- ♪ I don't care ♪
- People would pay top dollar
for us to undo a potentially
life-ruining sentence.
♪ I'll get by ♪
I think we should only
use our powers for good.
What are we considering good as of...
- 9:06 p.m. tonight?
- You know what?
It's like Potter Stewart said.
We'll know it when we see it.
[SINGING CONTINUES]
[CLEARS THROAT]
We just drove 300 miles
to scam Lubbock, Texas,
so that your client can have
a 13% bigger bank branch.
Don't get me wrong.
I loved every second of it.
But how is that using
our powers for good?
♪ As long as I ♪
♪ As long as I have you ♪
♪ And if the sky ♪
Okay. Fine.
Yeah. We'll know it when we see it.
I-I like it.
It's a plan I can get behind.
♪ ...the sea ♪
♪ Oh, just, just as... ♪
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[SPEAKING GERMAN]
Mm-hmm. Okay.
[FOOTSTEPS CLUNKING]
[AIR BRAKES SQUEALING]
I'm in position.
We're almost ready here. Stand by.
Copy.
[CONVERSING IN GERMAN]
What's up?
My apologies.
We have a small problem.
How small?
KAI: The red light.
It means there's no,
uh... How do you say...
Continuity on the circuit
of one of the three charges.
The orange one.
There may be a loose or faulty wire.
I'll go in and check.
I thought you were
the demolition expert.
It's my job, Michael.
- [SIGHS]
- Stand by.
Copy. Standing by.
[HATCH CREAKING]
[HATCH THUDS]
[FLASHLIGHT CLICKS]
[SNIFFLES]
[GASPING RAPIDLY]
♪ ♪
[GASPING CONTINUES]
[SPEAKING GERMAN] _
_
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
♪ ♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GASPING RAPIDLY]
♪ ♪
[GASPING CONTINUES]
[COUGHING]
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
[SIGHS]
[SPEAKS GERMAN] _
I think we're ready here, Michael.
All green.
We're good here.
- TYRUS: Ready?
- Go.
Call it.
On the go.
[AIR BRAKES HISS]
♪ ♪
Five...
four...
three...
two...
one.
Now!
[MUFFLED EXPLOSION]
[TRUCK THUDDING]
[ALL CHEERING]
[LAUGHTER]
Whoo-hoo!
[CONVERSATIONS IN GERMAN]
[MEN CHEERING, LAUGHING]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, wait!
We're missing one!
Have a drink!
No, no, no, no. I'm good. Thank you.
No. We don't accept this.
You can't be always on duty, Mike.
[MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
ALL: Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike!
Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike!
Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike!
[SPEAKS GERMAN] _
[MEN CHEER]
Ahh.
[CONVERSING IN GERMAN]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
♪ ♪
What's on your mind, hmm?
Nothing, really.
[SIGHS]
I'm pleased the blasting went well.
No damage to the structure,
no unforeseen incidents.
You don't seem pleased.
I'm just tired.
I need to know what's going on.
Nothing is going on.
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
This work is taking
longer than I estimated.
- It is.
- And I appreciate the R and R.
The boys... [CHUCKLING] they had fun.
But I'm...
[SIGHS]
Michael, you were married?
I was.
How long?
22 years.
Perhaps you will understand.
- 26 in April.
- Congratulations.
Mm-hmm.
My wife.
I'm...
[SIGHS]
Uh, I'm... Without her, I am adr...
Adrift.
Yeah. Adrift without her.
You've been away before.
Yes, of course. Not like this.
I'll finish what I've started,
no question of that.
Still, I can't help but wonder...
No, of course not.
- What?
- It's impossible.
Although...
Kai could supervise the
work until I get back.
I don't wish to cause you hardship,
even though I'd only be gone
for four days or five, maybe, total.
You're talking about flying
to Germany for a weekend?
Just a quick trip.
Fwih, fwih!
I could leave detailed instructions.
The work would not be interrupted.
You wanna see your wife?
More than anything.
Then finish the job.
Werner, you can do this.
You put your head down, and
you push your way through.
When it's done,
from the money you've made here,
you'll never be away
from your wife again.
Of course. [CHUCKLES]
Of course you're right.
Flight of fancy.
I-I tell you what.
We'll get you on the phone with her
for an extra call.
Mm.
We'll do it tomorrow.
Thank you, my friend.
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
You hang in there.
- [KNOCK ON DOOR]
- Mr. Fring?
Ah, yes, Lyle?
There's a, uh, man who just came in.
And I know that it's been a while,
but I was just like,
"He is so familiar."
I think it's one of
the guys that, you know,
made all the trouble last year.
[GULPS] Not, uh, the... the main guy,
which is why I'm not totally sure.
I see.
He's not doing anything, though.
Uh, he and the other
guy ordered some food,
and they're just sitting,
but I... I thought
that you'd want to know.
Oh, thank you, Lyle.
I'll take care of it.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
LALO: And you should know because...
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
Is everything to your liking?
Are you kidding me?
This is the best
chicken I have ever had.
[CHUCKLING] Well,
I'm delighted to hear that.
No, really. I'm serious.
I mean, it's crispy,
but it's not dried out,
and the seasoning... It's so...
flavorful.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Well, thank you.
Is there anything else I can do for you?
Is there any chance...
And I know the answer is probably no,
but is it possible for
me to meet the owner?
I am the owner.
Really?
How lucky for me.
Would you be interested in franchising?
Because I would be eager to invest.
Well, perhaps we should go to my office,
where we can discuss it further.
Excellent.
- Don't waste that.
- This way.
[FOOTSTEPS DEPART]
Now, what may I do for you, Señor...
Salamanca.
Eduardo Salamanca.
But you can call me "Lalo."
And you're Gustavo Fring.
I have been an admirer
of yours for many years.
You have how many of these restaurants?
- Seven.
And starting from nothing.
That's incredible.
What may I do for you?
I come here on behalf of my entire family
to give you our deepest thanks.
Well, for what?
For what?
For saving Don Hector's life.
I just visited him.
You know, seeing a man like that...
Can't speak, can barely move...
I wanted to weep.
But it could have been worse.
Varga tells me
that while everybody else
was picking their asses,
you rushed to him,
struck him on the chest,
and brought him back.
It was simple instinct.
But still, with all the
history between you two,
what you did was a gesture of peace.
Or at least, that's how we see it.
Mm.
I'm very pleased to hear that.
And here we are, gettin' along.
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
Mm.
_
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
Really?
Still, if we were to get along too well,
I'm sure Eladio wouldn't
like that, would he?
[INHALES SHARPLY]
I am satisfied with the
current arrangement.
I'm just shitting you.
You would be crazy to
go up against Eladio.
Look, I'm gonna be in town for a while,
so, uh, you know, we'll talk some more.
[SIGHS]
We owe you.
If you need a favor, I'm your man.
Same.
Naturally.
Oh, and I'll be back
for that chicken, eh?
It's too tasty to stay away from.
- [DOOR OPENS]
- [BREATHES DEEPLY]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[ENGINE STARTS, VEHICLE DEPARTS]
[KEYS JINGLING]
You say you pick up six keys a week?
NACHO: Yeah.
Where?
He's got a chicken farm way out of town.
Show me.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Mr. McGill, we're ready for you now.
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- Great.
CHAIRMAN: And it looks
like you've completed
the Pre Prosecution Diversion Program?
That's right... 3 1/2 weeks ago.
Actually, I believe,
if you look at the supplemental materials,
there's a letter from my
supervisor, Brad Markham.
Mm. Uh... ah, good.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
He says he was impressed
with your commitment.
And for most of last year,
you've been employed at CC Mobile?
It's a cellphone store.
And, again, there's a letter
from my manager, Mr. Robert Finn.
Uh, it's also in the
supplemental materials.
WOMAN: Mm.
Says here you were part of something
called the Silver Circle
three months in a row?
It's a sales award.
Mr. Finn and the people at CC Mobile
have been very generous.
You don't have to sell many phones
to get in the Silver, believe me.
[CHUCKLES]
What made you choose
that particular field?
Honestly, just, uh, to
put bread on the table.
But I would say it's given me
a new outlook on client relations.
I mean, after dealing
with cellphone contracts,
explaining statutes to my
clients should be a cakewalk.
[LIGHT LAUGHTER]
Well, as the saying goes,
the law is constantly changing.
Have you been keeping yourself, uh,
apprised of the latest developments?
I've been reading the Bar Journal.
You know, what caught my eye recently
was Crawford v. Washington.
Any of you follow that?
That has to do with the admissibility
of ex parte examinations?
That was a-a Supreme
Court case, wasn't it?
JIMMY: That's right. How did it go?
"The only indicium of reliability
sufficient to satisfy
constitutional demands
is the one the Constitution
actually prescribes...
Confrontation."
Classic Scalia.
I can't help but think about victims
forced to confront their
assailants in open court,
but on the other hand,
the Sixth Amendment
is pretty controlling.
Uh... [CLEARS THROAT] I'm sorry.
I just... I get rolling on
constitutional questions.
Short answer... I've been
doing my level best.
[CHUCKLES]
Well, Mr. McGill, is there
anything you'd like to tell us
about the reasons you were
suspended in the first place?
This past year,
that's pretty much been
the only thing on my mind.
And I'm humbled by the sheer
stupidity of my actions.
Remorse doesn't begin to cover it.
I'm not gonna make excuses
'cause there's no excuse for what I did.
But as I sit here,
I can assure you nothing like
that will ever happen again.
Never.
Well, all right.
That would seem to be satisfactory.
Um, Meg, you have something?
Mr. McGill, what does
the law mean to you?
The law?
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
Uh, yeah. Okay.
[SIGHS]
Um...
Listen, growing up,
becoming a lawyer was, uh,
the last thing on my mind.
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
Even if I wanted to, I
didn't have the smarts
or the skills or the
"stick-to-it" -ivness.
But I happened to get a
job with some attorneys,
and I couldn't help but
think, "Maybe I could do that?"
Something inside me made me want to try.
Now, listen, my diploma says
the "University of
American Samoa Law School,"
and that's exactly what it sounds like.
That's a correspondence school.
I wish it said "Georgetown"
[CHUCKLES] or "Northwestern."
But UAS... that's the only
one that would take me.
'Cause let me tell
you, I wasn't a natural.
I mean, the classes, the studying,
trying to pass the bar
[SCOFFS] practically killed me.
I must have quit 10 or 12 times.
But I kept coming back to it,
and I'm... I'm really glad I did
because when I got to
work with actual clients,
there was nothing else like it.
Our legal system is complicated,
and sometimes it could feel capricious,
but it's the closest thing to
real justice that we've got.
And for it to work,
it needs vigorous, passionate advocates.
And helping my clients, you know,
arguing on their behalf...
That's the best thing I've ever done.
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
And this past year...
I've missed the hell out of it.
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
That was very eloquent.
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
Was there any particular
influence on your views?
[SIGHS]
Um, credit where credit is due.
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
The University of American Samoa.
Go, Land Crabs!
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
Anything else?
No.
- Thank you.
- No? Good.
I think we have everything we need.
You'll be getting a
letter with our decision
in the next few days.
All right.
Um, thanks for your time, all of you.
[SIGHS]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
I thought he was right
up there, you know?
Yeah, no, he was part
of the review process.
And you've worked with him before.
- Good guy?
- Yeah, real good guy.
Hey. Hi.
- Hi. Mr. McGill.
- Yes.
I know they said I'd hear from them,
but, uh, just between you and me,
uh, what did they decide?
You got to be kidding me.
No. No. No, no, no, no, no!
[GROANS] Oh, no!
[DOOR BANGS]
[FOOTSTEPS DEPART]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACH]
Hey, wait a minute!
You're denying me?!
- What did I do wrong?
- Mr. McGill?
- What did I do wrong?!
- I can't...
Mr.... Mr. McGill,
this is not the place.
Okay. I did everything
right. Please tell me.
[SIGHS]
Look, [SIGHS] these
decisions are never easy.
Okay, come on. I deserve an answer.
[EXHALES SHARPLY, STAMMERS]
- Please!
- Mr. McGill, I-I can't...
I did everything right.
It was a question of sincerity.
A w-what?
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
Some members of the committee
found you somewhat...
insincere.
You're free to apply again next year.
[FOOTSTEPS DEPART]
[EXHALING SHARPLY]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [CONVERSATIONS IN GERMAN]
- [DOOR OPENS]
Hey, Mike.
Hey.
Well, how goes it with
the dirty half-dozen?
Playing volleyball.
That guy Kai cheats.
Mm-hmm.
Werner still talking?
Oh, they've been saying goodbye
for about 20 minutes now.
Anything of note?
Uh, they got a new puppy,
and it's peeing everywhere.
The dog, the house.
Her back's acting up, so they want
to go to the springs at
Baden-Baden once he gets back.
- Sound like the usual.
- Yep.
They've been at it
almost an hour and a half.
You want me to, uh,
give a 10-minute warning?
No.
Let him go on as long as he wants.
Wait. Okay.
They're wrapping up.
She's got to get to book club.
Mm.
[CONVERSATION CONTINUES]
I'm gonna check the perimeter.
[DOOR CREAKS, CLOSES]
[BALL BOUNCING, MEN SHOUTING IN GERMAN]
♪ ♪
[MAN SHOUTING IN GERMAN]
Ahh!
[HANDS CLAPPING]
[CONVERSATIONS IN GERMAN]
♪ ♪
TROY: We have no problem with
that language and will adjust.
We do have a concern
on page 15, clause 4b.
- [BLOWS]
- Third paragraph begins,
"The right to indemnification,
payment, reimbursement."
- Everyone with me?
- PAIGE: Yes. I see it.
This is clearly a
pro-sandbagging clause.
Troy, it simply gives us
the right to indemnification
for breaches of representation.
MAN: Of which there are none.
We feel it's necessary,
given the fast pace of
the negotiations thus far
and the lack of time we've
had to complete due diligence.
Mesa Verde set the pace here.
Further, you're overstepping
by requiring parts of the target payment
be put aside as collateral.
Kim Wexler here. If I may
respectfully remind you,
Mesa Verde is allowing
you to keep a clause
that warranty breaches must
be in a material respect.
It's standard language.
Y... As is ours.
Come on. Guys, meet me halfway here.
Fine.
Then we'd like to discuss
how we're defining "knowledge"
within the contract.
- [CELLPHONE VIBRATING]
- PAIGE: Be my guest.
We feel that what we've established
is pretty reasonable.
- Our clients would like to propose...
- Hey there.
...changing "within
the seller's knowledge"
to "to the best of the
seller's knowledge."
Slow down.
[ENGINE REVS, TIRES SCREECHING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[SCREECHING CONTINUES]
[KEYS JINGLING, CAR DOOR OPENS]
- [CAR DOOR SLAMS]
- Insincere! Insincere?!
- Jimmy, what happened?
- A goddamn year?
What am I supposed to
do for a whole year?!
- Jimmy...
- I can guarantee you
I'm not selling cellphones
for a fuckin' year.
- I'll tell you that.
- What did they say, exactly?
- How... How did it...
- [GROANS] Hard pass!
- All right.
- And don't tell me I can appeal
because once the board hears the
word "insincere," I'm screwed.
- Jimmy... Jimmy...
- How do you disprove "insincere"?!
Please, Jimmy, just take a breath
and start from the beginning, please.
I was good, Kim.
I mean, I-I wasn't stuck up,
but I knew my shit, right?
"What have you been doing
during your suspension?"
and, uh, "Have you been
keeping up with the law?"
Yadda yadda. All fine.
And then one of them, out of nowhere,
comes up with this weird-ass question...
"What does the law mean to you?"
That's a big one.
Huge! And I nailed it!
I talked about the meaning of the law
and I was down-to-earth
and I was humble
and I was sincere and they loved it.
So...
So they turned me down.
Well, there has to be
more to it than that.
There's not.
I don't... [STAMMERS]
What did they say when
you talked about Chuck?
[SCOFFS] What does Chuck
have to do with this?
What?
Well, so, you didn't even...
Why would I?
Okay. O... Um...
Okay, listen, we will figure this out.
And, yes, you will appeal.
We'll appeal this to the...
- They're just gonna rubber-stamp...
- Well, we won't let them.
- They're gonna rubber-stamp whatever...
- And we'll find a way to make you look sincere.
- Kim, I was sincere!
- I know that.
- I meant we will fix it.
- I might have been
a little corny, but
I meant every word.
I know that.
You don't believe me.
- Of course I do.
- Jesus.
It's right there on your face.
You think I'm some kind of
lowlife, some kind of asshole...
- What?
- ...the kind of lawyer guilty people hire, right?
No. Jimmy, that's not...
Yeah, you look at me, and
you see Slippin' Jimmy.
I never said that.
Yeah, but you thought it!
You want to know why the
committee called you insincere?
Because you didn't mention Chuck.
What does that have to even...
They read the transcripts.
They know what happened, Jimmy.
They were waiting for you to
say something about him.
So I'm supposed to make a big hairy deal
about my dead brother at
my re-instatement hearing?
How is that sincere?
Ya, I don't think about Chuck, okay?
I don't miss Chuck.
Chuck was alive and now
he's dead and that's that.
Finito. Life goes on. So sue me.
There it is again. [STAMMERS]
- That's why we don't have an office.
- What? No!
Just, you know, do not
start in on that office.
I don't want to hear another word
about that stupid office.
Stupid office? Okay.
Here we go. Here we go.
Jimmy, I have been on your
side since the day we met!
Who comes running when you call?
Who cleans up your messes?
I have a job,
but I drop everything
for you every single time.
You confess to a felony on tape,
I'm there.
You have a bar hearing, I represent you.
Over and over again, if
you need me, I'm there.
But somehow in your
mind the only measure
of my feelings for you
is... is some office?!
I'm good enough to live
with, to sleep with,
but God forbid you should
have an office with me.
- What are you t... I just told you...
- You get a little bored with your life,
so you come down and
roll around in the dirt...
- have some fun with Slippin' Jimmy...
- Oh, is it fun?
- ...and then it's [CLICKS TONGUE] back up.
- Fun like lying to the ADA
to get your friend out of the shitter?
Or fun like standing there with
a smile plastered on my face
while you play infantile
mind games on my law partner?
Oh, what a mistake it was
to take me up to your office in the sky!
- You'll never do that again!
- Yeah, maybe I won't.
And maybe next time
you call, I won't come.
There you go. Kick a man when he's down.
Jimmy, you are always down.
[SCOFFS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[LOCK DISENGAGES, DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CREAKS, CLOSES]
[KEYS JINGLE]
[SHOES SQUEAKING]
[BAG THUDS, KEYS JINGLE]
[UNZIPPING]
[RUSTLING]
[DRAWER OPENS]
[SIGHS]
[OBJECTS CLATTERING]
[BOOKS THUDDING]
[SIGHS]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
I messed it all up.
You still want to be a lawyer?
Yeah.
Well, we can start with that.
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
[DOOR SQUEAKS]
ARTHUR: Hey, Mike.
Hey.
Thanks.
Oh, thank you, sir.
So, what do we got?
It's pretty quiet.
Kai was up late again.
About an hour after he went down,
Werner came out for a couple minutes.
Then Casper was up around 2:30,
watched some TV, headed back in.
What's going on with 6?
Huh?
There... What is that?
Oh, yeah. Dead pixels.
Wasn't there yesterday.
Had a voltage spike earlier.
Camera flared for about 20 seconds,
but it came right back.
A voltage spike?
Any of the other cameras do that?
Uh...
[MOUSE CLICKING]
Yeah. 10.
Show me the outside cameras.
[MOUSE CLICKS]
Oh.
You... let's go.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR BUZZES]
Get the lights!
♪ ♪
[POWER SURGING]
Up there. You check that out.
- [CHATTER]
- KAI: What's going on?
Mike?
♪ ♪
[LOCK CLATTERS]
[DEVICE BEEPS]
[ELECTRICITY HUMMING]
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --