Previously on "Better Call Saul"...
We can't just keep 'em alive.
We gotta keep 'em
from climbing the walls.
Work starts tomorrow night.
I believe you will wake, Hector.
JIMMY: I need to be able
to sell my phones
without worrying
about getting ripped off.
- [TELEPHONE RINGS]
- KIM: They want me to run
their banking division.
The thing is, it'll keep paying the bills
and free me up to do
the work I really care about.
JIMMY: I have been thinking
about criminal law myself.
You have to do what's best for you.
Kim, you gotta do what's best for you.
♪♪
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[JIMMY SIGHS]
[FAUCET TURNS ON]
- [TOOTHBRUSH TAPS]
- [SNIFFS]
- [FAUCET TURNS OFF]
- [FAUCET TURNS ON]
[TOOTHBRUSH TAPS]
[FAUCET TURNS OFF]
[FAUCET TURNS ON AND OFF]
[RHYTHMIC CLAPPING]
[LOLA MARSH'S "SOMETHING STUPID" PLAYS]
[FAUCET TURNS ON]
[SPITS]
♪♪
[FAUCET TURNS OFF]
♪ I know I stand in line
until you think ♪
♪ You have the time to spend
an evening with me ♪
[BALL THUDS]
That chair.
♪ And if we go someplace to dance ♪
♪ I know that there's a chance
you won't be leaving with me ♪
♪♪
♪ Then afterwards we drop
into a quiet little, place ♪
♪ And have a drink or two ♪
♪♪
♪ And then I go and spoil it all ♪
♪ By saying something stupid
like "I love you" ♪
Okay. Great.
There's just, uh,
some more boxes in the back...
♪ I can see it in your eyes that you ♪
♪ Despise the same old lies
you heard the night before ♪
♪♪
♪ And though it's just a line to you ♪
♪ For me it's true and never seemed ♪
- ♪ So right before ♪
- [SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
♪♪
♪ I practice every day to find
some clever lines to say ♪
- ♪ To make the meaning come through ♪
- [PRINTER BEEPING]
♪♪
♪ But then I think I'll wait
until the evening gets late ♪
♪ And I'm alone with you ♪
♪♪
♪ The time is right,
your perfume fills my head ♪
♪ The stars get red,
and, oh, the night's so blue ♪
♪♪
♪ And then I go and spoil it all ♪
♪ By saying something stupid
like "I love you" ♪
♪♪
- [SPITS]
- [FAUCET TURNS ON]
♪♪
[FAUCET TURNS ON]
- [SPITS]
- [FAUCET TURNS OFF]
♪♪
- [SAW BUZZING]
- [JUICER WHIRRING]
♪ The time is right,
your perfume fills my head ♪
♪ The stars get red,
and, oh, the night's so blue ♪
♪♪
♪ And then I go and spoil it all ♪
♪ By saying something stupid
like "I love you" ♪
♪♪
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[BRAKES SCREECH]
♪♪
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
[CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE]
♪♪
♪ I can see it in your eyes that you ♪
♪ Despise the same old lies
you heard the night before ♪
[PRINTER BEEPING]
♪ And though it's just a line to you ♪
♪ For me it's true and never
seemed so right before ♪
♪♪
♪ I practice every day to find
some clever lines to say ♪
♪ To make the meaning come through ♪
♪♪
♪ But then I think I'll wait ♪
- ♪ Until the evening gets late ♪
- [FAUCET TURNS ON]
♪ And I'm alone with you ♪
[FAUCET SHUTS OFF]
♪ The time is right,
your perfume fills my head ♪
♪ The stars get red,
and, oh, the night's so blue ♪
[PRINTER BEEPING]
♪ And then I go and spoil it all ♪
♪ By saying something stupid
like "I love you" ♪
[DRAWER CLOSES]
♪ I love you ♪
[SPOON CLINKS]
♪♪
[RHYTHMIC CLAPPING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
[SIGHS]
[SLURPS]
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[SIGHS]
[VEHICLE PASSING IN DISTANCE]
♪♪
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
You made it. Come on in.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
Picture a reception desk
right here, right?
It's always nice to be greeted
by a friendly face.
Now, over in this corner,
we got a fireplace
with a cozy waiting area,
couch, couple chairs,
water cooler, electric kettle,
maybe an assortment of teas.
This is my office in here.
Guess what?
These are all original fixtures.
So, that's...
Uh, we're four blocks
from the courthouse here.
So, how convenient is that?
Now, there's a bathroom,
and it's... it's cute.
[CHUCKLES] Uh...
- [DOOR CREAKS]
- [EXHALES SHARPLY]
Whew.
We're gonna get that cleaned out.
Um, there's a shower in there,
when you're buried in discovery
late at night.
This is for the partner. Corner office.
Lots of natural light,
and that's great
for your circadian rhythms.
Uh... [SIGHS]
Cherry blossoms. That's nice.
And, uh...
One, two, three, four, five, six.
It's pretty big.
Um, there's a kitchenette down the hall.
Uh, it's kind of perfect for snacks
or, uh, BYO lunch. [SIGHS]
Get one of those snazzy Keurigs,
put that in there.
Stick a few potted plants around,
make the place nice.
What do you think?
[SIGHS]
So, no more cellphones?
No, but this is what the phones were for.
So, if you were a lawyer,
this would be a great place, right?
If I was a lawyer?
Nope.
Big glass high-rise, 40th floor.
Big glass high-rise.
Yeah.
When I'm not on my boat.
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
Hmm?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
Excellent.
[INDISTINCT SPEAKING OVER P.A.]
[CART RATTLING IN DISTANCE]
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Muy bien.
Oh, uh, let's just hold off
on lunch for a few minutes.
Just... Just set the tray on the side.
Of course, Doctor.
BRUCKNER: [SPEAKING SPANISH] _
[TRAY THUDS]
[PEN SCRATCHING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[CUP CLATTERS]
Sorry. I'll take care of that.
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
[PAPER TOWELS SWISHING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS IN DISTANCE]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[PITCHER THUDS]
Bueno. Continuemos.
Hector?
Hector... [SPEAKING SPANISH] _
Hmm? Muy bien.
[INDISTINCT SPEAKING OVER P.A.,
TELEPHONE RINGING]
Este...
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
[VEHICLE PASSES]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[SIGHS, SUCKS LIP]
Anyone in particular
you want me to talk to?
Or not talk to?
[CHUCKLES] Talk to anyone.
Really, just... just have fun.
[CHUCKLES] Don't worry.
They're gonna love you.
- Yeah. Hi. How are you?
- This is Jimmy McGill.
- Yeah.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Welcome.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
- Great to meet you.
Ron, this is Jimmy McGill.
Oh, hi, Ron.
Hey, Jimmy. Great to meet you.
Hey, got to say,
I'm obsessed with your tie.
[MID-TEMPO JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING]
KIM: No? [CHUCKLING] Okay.
Oh, excuse me one second.
Hey, guys. Jimmy,
this is, uh, Gary and Stef.
They... They work on Mesa Verde with me.
Famous Gary and the famous-er Stef.
- Hi.
- [CHUCKLES]
Kim says you're the absolute best.
- [LIGHT LAUGHTER]
- I can't. Ate a lot of cake.
Oh, whoa! Here it is!
This is for us. Debbie, one for you.
There you go. One for Zack.
- Thank you.
- One for Viola. And you know what?
Two for Lewis
'cause he skipped lunch to work!
Aw, really?
[MID-TEMPO JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[CLICKS TONGUE, BREATHES DEEPLY]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[ICE CLINKING SOFTLY]
♪♪
1, 2, 3, 4,
5, 6, 7,
8, 9, 10.
[WALL THUDS]
[SIGHS]
♪♪
[LAUGHTER IN DISTANCE]
[ICE CUBES CLINKING]
♪♪
[SIGHS]
- Are you taking votes?
- Yes.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
- Was Jill there? At the retreat?
- No. Oh, Lord.
- No. Uh, she came later.
- Oh, okay.
- She was a client.
- Really?
- Oh, yeah.
- Do you guys do theater retreats?
No, absolutely not.
SCHWEIKART: I think it might
be a little different this year
- not sweating with your co-workers.
- [LAUGHTER]
I heard Packard-Kilber
is taking their whole company
to a resort outside of Santa Fe.
- It's pretty... pretty ritzy.
- Mm.
Oh, we're just talking
about company retreats.
Oh. That's a great idea.
Where we going?
[CHUCKLES] Sorry, pal. Employees only.
Oh, darn it.
[LIGHT LAUGHTER]
I'm thinking of splurging
a little this year.
You know, don't want to be
outdone by the competition.
You know, word gets out
you're a cheapskate.
[CHUCKLES] Sure, sure.
That's hard to shake off.
[CHUCKLES] I've... I've heard
Ten Thousand Waves
is supposed to be amazing.
I love that place.
Or Carlsbad Caverns.
I still think that Taos is number one.
I love a ski trip.
And I think it'd be good
for team building.
Taos is... nice.
[SMACKS LIPS]
Feel free to jump in.
[CHUCKLING] We're just spit-balling here.
[CHUCKLES]
I don't... [CHUCKLING] I mean...
Well, I mean, if you're up
for adventure...
[CHUCKLES] ...you know
where the great skiing is?
Well, it's Telluride.
- Hmm.
- Yes.
Oh, okay. It's kind of
a long drive, isn't it?
Uh, that could be...
part of the fun, you know?
Uh, rent one of those, uh,
fancy party buses.
Stick "Sound of Music" on the TVs,
and everybody sings along.
Pretty soon, you're there.
And I got to say,
the runs at Telluride...
they make Taos look like a bunny slope.
Telluride, huh?
It... It's worth considering.
Mm. And parkas.
Everybody's got to have parkas.
[CHUCKLES] Of course.
No. I'm talking custom parkas.
Uh, two words... client development.
They see all of you out there
cutting the powder
in your matching
Schweikart and Cokely parkas.
Well, you're gonna make an impression.
You will thank me later. [CLICKS TONGUE]
You certainly don't think small.
[CHUCKLES]
Shit. You know what?
Aspen...
That's where you want to go.
Hey, Aspen is like Telluride on steroids.
You got shopping.
You got restaurants and spas.
And talk about client development.
It's a billionaire's playground.
- Mm.
- Yeah.
Jimmy, Aspen is like
a nine-hour bus ride.
Yeah. You're right.
You're right. Nine hours.
That... That is a long time
to be sitting on a bus.
Yes, it is.
But what's that I hear?
[IMITATES ENGINE RUMBLING]
"I'm a private chartered jet!
And I'm sorry. I'm very busy right now.
I'm transporting
56 distinguished attorneys
to their amazing destination.
Aspen, here we come!"
[LAUGHTER]
Come on, Rich! You're gonna love it!
[VEHICLE PASSES]
[SIGHS]
Well, that was something.
Yup.
[VEHICLE PASSES]
[RADIO TURNS ON]
[THE BREEDERS' "NO ALOHA" PLAYS]
♪♪
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[BURL IVES' "BIG ROCK
CANDY MOUNTAIN" PLAYS]
[TRUCK BEEPING]
♪♪
♪ Oh, the buzzin' of the bees
in the cigarette trees ♪
♪ The soda water fountain ♪
♪ Where the lemonade springs
and the bluebird sings ♪
♪ In that Big Rock Candy Mountain ♪
♪♪
- ♪ On a summer's day
- [DOOR BUZZES, SLAMS]
In the month of May ♪
♪ A burly bum come a-hiking ♪
♪ Down a shady lane near the sugar cane ♪
♪ He was looking for his liking ♪
♪ As he strolled along, he sung a song ♪
- ♪ Of the land of milk and honey ♪
- Just a sec.
♪ Where a bum can stay for many a day ♪
♪ And he won't need any money ♪
[DOOR CLOSES]
♪ Oh, oh, oh, ohh ♪
- [TIMECARD CLOCK CLACKS]
- [TRUCK BEEPING]
♪ The bu-u-u-u-zzin' of the bees
in the cigarette trees ♪
♪ The soda water fountain ♪
♪ Where the lemonade springs
and the bluebird sings ♪
- ♪ In that Big Rock Candy Mountain ♪
- [DOOR CLOSES]
♪♪
♪ In the Big Rock Candy Mountain ♪
♪ The cops have wooden legs ♪
♪ The bulldogs all have rubber teeth ♪
♪ And the hens lay soft-boiled eggs ♪
♪ The farmers' trees are full of fruit ♪
- [WHIRRING]
- ♪ The barns are full of hay ♪
♪ I want to go
where there ain't no snow ♪
♪ Where the sleet don't fall ♪
♪ And the wind don't blow ♪
- [ZIPPER OPENS]
- ♪ In that Big Rock Candy Mountain ♪
[FLASHLIGHT CLICKS]
♪ Oh, the bu-u-u-u-zzin' of the bees ♪
♪ In the cigarette trees ♪
♪ The soda water fountain ♪
♪ Where the lemonade springs
and the bluebird sings ♪
♪ In that Big Rock Candy Mountain ♪
♪ Oh ♪
- [GRATE CREAKING]
- ♪ Oh, oh, ohh ♪
[GRATE THUDS]
♪ The bu-u-u-u-zzin' of the bees ♪
♪ In the cigarette trees ♪
♪ The soda water fountain ♪
♪ Where the lemonade springs
and the bluebird sings ♪
♪ In that Big Rock Candy Mountain ♪
[BOOTS THUDDING]
[SWITCH CLICKS, LIGHTS CLACK]
[GAS HISSING]
BRUCKNER: He's making progress
on the Stroke Scale.
He started at a 30,
and that number is steadily coming down.
He's at a 22 right now.
And he's made modest improvement
in his ataxia, which is loss of...
Loss of body movement. Yes.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
- [SPOON CLACKS]
- Well, this all sounds quite positive.
[KNIFE CHOPPING]
But you know
the question that I will ask.
Is it him?
Is it the Hector Salamanca you knew?
- [LIQUID BUBBLING]
- [CRICKETS CHIRPING]
I think at this point, that's
almost a philosophical question.
What I can tell you
is that he's more responsive.
He's making incremental
improvements almost every day.
I think if you see the evidence,
you'll be very encouraged.
[KNIFE CLACKS]
You'll see this was an
especially productive session.
Mm.
[BRUCKNER SPEAKING SPANISH]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
- [FINGER TAPS]
- Muy bien.
I know it may seem like a small thing.
That same exchange
would have taken
four times as long a month ago,
and a month before that,
he couldn't respond at all.
All his vital signs have improved.
Also, I've been tracking his
progress using the SIS,
with particular focus on hand mobility
since that's his mode of communication.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
[CUP CLATTERS]
- NURSE: Sorry. I'll take care of that.
- Has he done that before?
- The cup?
- Mm.
That was likely an involuntary movement.
[TAPE REWINDING]
[TAPE CLICKS]
[PAPER TOWEL CRUNCHES, SWISHES]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
♪♪
Do you think that was purposeful?
- [BREATHES DEEPLY]
- [REMOTE CLICKS]
You've done magnificent work.
Oh. Thank you.
I understand
that construction on your clinic
is nearly complete.
I trust the work
is to your specifications?
That's putting it mildly.
The new wing is simply extraordinary.
We'll be able to care
for so many patients
who would have been tossed aside.
I've kept you from your work long enough.
Oh.
It is time to delegate
Mr. Salamanca's care.
His recovery has been remarkable.
And my gratitude to you is beyond words.
Are you sure?
Hector's progress is very promising.
With sustained, intensive care,
he may eventually learn
how to talk and even walk again.
[SMACKS LIPS]
Hmm. Perhaps we should
temper our expectations.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
I believe the paila marina is ready.
[TV TURNS OFF]
[VEHICLE PASSING]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING, METAL CLANGING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[TOOLS WHIRRING]
WERNER: Now that the boys have
built the concrete forms,
we are nearly ready to pour the walls.
And when's that going to happen?
First, there must be one more blast.
I thought we were done with that.
Almost done, yes.
But we must clear that rock
to make way for the elevator shaft,
just one more,
carefully shaped to keep
from damaging the work.
- [VEHICLE BEEPING]
- And how big a pop are we talking about?
[MAN SHOUTING IN GERMAN]
[METAL GROANS]
[CONCRETE CRUMBLES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
KAI: [SPEAKING GERMAN]
[SPEAKING GERMAN] _
Scheisse!
Hey, asshole...
[SPEAKING GERMAN] _
[SPEAKING GERMAN]
[ALL SHOUTING IN GERMAN]
- [WHISTLES]
- [SPEAKING GERMAN] _
[GRUNTS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GROANS]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
[HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO]
- [BRAKES SCREECH]
- Yo, Saul. Three.
♪♪
Coming right up.
There you go.
♪♪
See ya.
Yes, you will.
[MUSIC FADES]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[VEHICLES PASSING]
[TRAIN HORN BLOWS IN DISTANCE]
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF, CAR DOOR OPENS]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[BARKING CONTINUES]
[VEHICLE PASSING]
What can I do you for?
This you... Saul Goodman?
Uh, that's right, Officer.
[CHUCKLES]
You, uh... You want to know
where I got it?
Off a drug dealer who got sprung today
'cause he was using
a drop phone that you sold him.
[SMACKS LIPS] Huh.
Doesn't bother you that you're peddling
to a bunch of lowlifes who use
these things to sell drugs?
What my customers do with the phones
after they leave my possession...
that's their business.
Let me ask you a favor, all right?
Get your van out of here,
park it in front of
a grocery store in Corrales...
you know, someplace nice...
and... and sell there.
You know, I'm sure there's a lot of...
a lot of soccer moms
that can use some phones.
[CHUCKLING] I don't know.
I think my customer base is right here.
Get some new customers.
I don't feel the need to.
See, I got a permit,
and I'm collecting sales tax,
and this is a legitimate business, right?
So anyone who wants to buy a
phone from me is free to do so.
I'm asking nicely, okay?
And I respectfully decline.
- You're gonna go this way, huh?
- There it is.
What's it gonna be?
What, it's gonna be littering
or rolling through a stop sign?
Hey, how about you plant
somethin'-somethin'
in my glove compartment?
You know what, pal?
Just take it easy, okay?
Maybe this is why people need privacy.
Maybe this is why they need my phones.
Maybe you're the problem.
Okay, so, as long as you make a buck,
the whole world
- can just go in the crapper?
- Yeah...
♪ I'm going back to big Mamou ♪
["BIG MAMOU" PLAYS IN HEADPHONES]
♪ I don't want my woman
telling me what to do ♪
♪♪
♪ Said Big Mamou ♪
- No, no, no! No, no, no!
- ♪ Said Big Mamou ♪
He's a cop!
♪ I said Big Mamou ♪
He's a cop.
[MUSIC CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY
IN HEADPHONES]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
MAN ON RADIO: 5-4-5, Central.
JIMMY: This was all just a mistake.
My friend got confused, okay?
He was just trying to do his job.
I hired him for security.
He was trying to protect me.
You're in plain clothes.
He had no idea you're a police officer.
Oh, he knew, all right.
How?
I picked him up three years ago.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Pickpocketing.
- [POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
- [STAMMERS]
Three years, that's a long time.
I mean, how can you be sure
it's the same guy?
Seriously?
Officer, look, you were right.
I was wrong.
[TRAIN HORN BLARES IN DISTANCE]
Were you, now?
Yes. And you know what else?
You will not see me out here
selling my phones ever again, right?
So just do me a favor.
Let's just shake hands, avoid the
paperwork, and we just go home.
Do ya a favor?
I was asking you for a favor.
Fair enough.
Oh, I asked you nicely,
and you told me to go screw myself.
I don't... I don't think
I used those words.
- [CAR DOOR OPENS]
- I...
See you around.
[CAR DOOR CLOSES, ENGINE STARTS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[ENGINE REVS]
[PINBALL MACHINE CLINKING, BELL DINGING]
- [INDISTINCT TV CHATTER]
- [DOOR BUZZES]
[DINGING CONTINUES]
[DOOR SLAMS]
[MAN SPEAKING GERMAN ON TV]
[BALL CLATTERING]
[PINBALL MACHINE DINGS]
[PINBALL MACHINE PLAYS SAD TONE]
Michael.
Glad that you can join me
for my happy hour.
Huh.
[PINBALL MACHINE DINGING]
It doesn't look so happy to me.
They'll feel better after...
how do you say it?
Uh, Mittagsschlaefchen?
When in kindergarten,
the whole class has a nice, little rest.
Uh, nap time.
Nap time. [CHUCKLES]
Good.
Now say "Mittagsschlaefchen."
Mittag...
Mittagsschlaefchen.
[CHUCKLES] Good. Good, Michael.
- Pilsner or the lager?
- Lager.
[SPEAKING GERMAN] _
[LIQUID SLOSHES]
_
[GLASS CLACKS]
He said you sound like a real Kraut.
How do you say "bullshit"?
Mm. "Bullshit."
- [TAP CREAKS]
- Yeah. That.
[MUG THUDS]
But, really, you're one of us, Michael.
[CROWD CHEERS ON TV]
"Ehrmantraut"... in German,
it comes from two words...
[SMACKS LIPS] "world" plus "strength."
Yeah, I guess.
What's the latest?
[PINBALL MACHINE DINGING]
Before we can continue,
we must build a new concrete form
and straighten the rebar.
I'm so sorry.
I'm happy to explain
the delay to Mr. Fring.
You don't worry about Mr. Fring.
He just wants to see it done right.
Let me ask you a question.
Of course.
What would happen if we sent Kai
back to Germany?
[INDISTINCT CHANTING ON TV]
[PINBALL MACHINE DINGING]
Not good.
Kai is my best demolition man.
Sure, he's a Grossmaul...
bah, bah, bah...
but he's a good boy.
They all are.
Well, maybe that's the problem.
They're boys.
Well, yes.
But we need young people to do this work.
Or maybe you and I will do it?
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
They thought they were going
to be here for eight months,
and they can see
we're not even halfway done.
You have done a wonderful job, Michael.
You brought everything we could ask for.
But you can't keep men
locked away forever.
They need fresh air,
a change of scenery and, uh...
You understand?
R and R.
Hmm?
Rest and relaxation.
[CHUCKLING] Precisely.
This is what they need... R and R.
Prost, Michael.
Prost.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[SIGHS]
2 1/2 years.
Yeah, they always go for the max.
Come on, now. They'll come down.
[SCOFFS] PD didn't make it
sound promising.
[CHUCKLES] The guy's...
He's just a burnout.
He's trying to soften you up
for an easy deal, all right?
There's no way you'd do
that kind of time.
You're goddamn right.
Wait. Uh, what... what do you mean?
I'mma bounce.
I got places I can go.
Ehhh. No. Uh, no, that's not
a good idea, Huell.
Better than going in.
[DOOR CLOSES IN DISTANCE]
Come on. You'll have a warrant on you.
And that shit doesn't go away.
You know, three years from now,
you're pulled over
for a broken taillight,
and now you're not
just a guy who shoved a cop.
You're a guy who shoved a cop and ran.
Well, I just won't drive
with a broken taillight.
Sooner or later,
they're gonna catch up with you.
They didn't catch D.B. Cooper.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS IN DISTANCE]
- [TELEPHONE RINGS]
- [SIGHS]
Why don't you, uh... Why don't
you give me a shot at this?
I-I think I can fix it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
What if I told you you're not going in?
Like not at all, not never?
'Cause that's what it's gonna take.
Yeah. Never. All right?
Just don't skip.
How you gonna do that?
You ain't even a lawyer.
A lawyer.
Dude, I don't need
to be a lawyer, all right?
[CHUCKLES] I'm a magic man.
Will you have a little faith in me?
[TELEPHONES RINGING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[HEELS CLACKING]
See, now, I-I would help Huell
myself if I could,
but I don't think
he's gonna wait around a month
for me to be reinstated.
Uh, you've been selling drop phones?
On the street?
Kim, I... I just... If we could, uh...
Look, Kim... here's what I'm thinking.
I did a little recon,
and the arresting officer...
he has a DUI, you know, eight years ago.
And he's been put on desk duty twice.
I know he has anger issues.
I can attest to it, right?
So, we get him smelling
like a distillery,
and we piss him off in court.
Now... Now, he will take the bait.
He will lose his cool
in front of the judge,
a little stumble in there
just for dramatic effect,
and I have some thoughts
on how to engineer that,
but you get the gist.
Next thing you know, case dismissed.
[STAMMERS]
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
Viola, can you get me case material
for penal code 34-22, sections 22 to 27?
Yeah. Battery on a PO.
Mm-hmm. Thanks.
[RECEIVER CLACKS]
Great. Uh, what's our first move?
I'm not tearing down a cop.
That's okay. You tell me.
I will look into this.
Not making any promises,
but if it is as bad as you say it is...
I don't know... maybe
there is something I could do.
[INHALES DEEPLY] Maybe.
[EXHALES SHARPLY] Uh...
Thanks, Kim.
Listen. I really appreciate it.
Okay.
And, um, tell me
if there's anything I can do.
Yep.
Oh, excuse me, Jimmy.
Oh, uh, Viola, can you just...
- Oh.
- Thank you.
[COINS CLINKING]
Oh, I got it.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
- [METAL DETECTOR WHINES]
- Hope that wasn't a bribe.
Wow. That would be one sad bribe.
[CHUCKLES] Not on my salary.
Do you have a minute to discuss a case?
[LIQUID POURS]
Sure. I got two minutes.
I can't help but think you guys
are reaching with this one.
Where have I heard that before?
Babineaux.
Babineaux? Really?
Doesn't seem like your kind of client.
I disagree.
To start with, the whole thing
was just a misunderstanding.
Pickpocket with a rap sheet
attacks a cop in broad daylight?
That's a misunderstanding?
Uh, I would not call it an attack.
Realistically, we should
be talking misdemeanor.
It's battery on a PO.
That's 18 months, plus a year...
Of bitch time.
I know what you're asking for.
It's excessive.
He has a prior.
The same officer arrested him
three years...
Three years ago, but Babineaux
didn't recognize him.
He... He didn't even know he was a cop.
The guy drove an unmarked car.
He was in plain clothes.
He... He had his back turned.
I'm sorry. I don't buy it.
Suzanne, I did my homework.
You have five other cases
where civilians were accused
of physical force
against police officers,
and not once were the defendants given
anything close to this kind of jail time.
They weren't repeat offenders.
State v. Murphy.
Daniel Murphy was homeless.
He was off his meds...
He head-butted a police officer.
He gave him a concussion.
Five months, suspended.
State v. Karp... five months, suspended.
- You're not seriously comparing...
- State v. Brezovich...
no jail time, two months probation.
No priors.
Brezovich broke a cop's nose.
This is unequal justice.
In this case, the officer
was not injured at all.
He was hit with a bag of sandwiches.
How can you justify giving
- Babineaux 18 months?
- Plus a year.
He has no history of violence.
There is no negotiation here, Kim.
And honestly,
I don't understand why you want
anything to do with this.
On one side, I've got
a decorated police officer doing his job.
On the other, you have
a professional thief
who threw him to the ground.
And their only witness
is a scumbag, disbarred lawyer
who peddles drop phones to criminals.
You don't know the whole story.
[FOLDER THUDS, LOCK ENGAGES]
[GATE CREAKS]
I'd rather talk to you in person.
Are you at home?
O-Okay.
Is there a good place to meet you?
Great. I can be there within an hour.
All right, Mr. Babineaux.
Sure. Huell.
Just sit tight. I'm on my way.
[CELLPHONE BEEPS]
I'm gonna go talk to him right now.
I need you to back my play.
Does that mean what I think it means?
He's gonna call you after I talk to him,
and you and I have to be
on the same page.
Huell can't run.
He's gonna have to put on his
big-boy pants and go to jail...
- [SIGHS] Shit.
- ...at least for a little while.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
There's no way around it?
He's not gonna do
what they're pushing for.
I promise you that.
But, yeah, no matter what, he's...
he's gonna have to do some time.
[CLICKS TONGUE, SIGHS]
Well, thanks for trying.
Jimmy, he can't jump bail.
You'll back me up, right?
Good.
I mean, if you say this is the only way
we can legitimately do this,
well, it's the only way.
So, you're gonna tell him to stay put?
Yeah. Sure.
You do your thing. I'll do mine.
Jimmy, come on. What does that mean?
[ENGINE STARTS]
Don't worry.
[GEARSHIFT CLICKS, ENGINE REVS]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[VEHICLES PASSING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ENGINE REVS]
♪♪
[CAR ALARM CHIRPS]
[VEHICLES PASSING]
♪♪
[OFFICE SUPPLIES CLATTER]
[PURSE UNZIPS]
[CASH REGISTER BEEPS]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
Jimmy, whatever you're doing, don't.
[CASH REGISTER BEEPS, KEYS CLACKING]
Ya I know, but... listen.
I have a better way.