Wuhu!
[distorted] ♪ The Simpsons ♪
Fellow heartbroken
environmentalists,
we've tried to find a place in Springfield
where something, anything, will grow.
And this could be the spot.
[crowd chattering]
Why am I optimistic about
this oil-stained Fury Road?
Because look,
something finally grew!
[crowd gasps]
[all gasping]
Oh, no, you don't.
I own this land, and I decide
what grows here. Nothing.
It was just a daisy.
Now disperse, you
tree-smooching trespassers,
unless you're staying for
tonight's hobo philharmonic.
[♪ playing "Symphony No. 5"]
Spoon section, on the
downbeat, am I hearing a fork?
[chuckles]
Why even try to plant flowers?
In this hideous town,
there's no point to anything.
[groans] Poor Lisa.
There's nothing harder than
when your kid's so depressed,
it slightly bums you out.
Excuse me, I couldn't
help but overhear.
I'm a child therapist who
specializes in ecological melancholy.
Ooh, fun job.
Look, Doc, I'll tell you
how to cure my depression.
Fix this horrible world!
Oh! You can't? Join the club.
No one can make a difference.
Don't give up hope, honey.
There's gotta be some new
high-tech therapy thing now
that you haven't tried.
AI is destroying everyone else's
career, can't it hollow out yours?
Oh, no. Not until far, far
into next month.
I've had great results lately
with these EMDR stimulators.
You hold each of these tappers in
your hands and they pulse gently,
helping the brain process
negative thoughts.
Sometimes they even send
people into a hypnogogic state.
I'm sorry,
but my mind's gonna need something
a little more sophisticated
than a couple of table buzzers
from TGI… [slurring] …Friday.
[♪ jazz music playing]
[Lisa] Whoa.
Where am I? This is
some good hypnagogia.
Our sax player is out.
Somehow he mixed up his
sugar and his opium.
Worst sugar allergy
I've ever seen.
How… How are we gonna get a new
sax player at the last minute?
Edith, you play, right?
Edith? You mean me?
Wow. This dream is
primo. Louis primo.
Might as well go with it.
[♪ jazz music continues]
Ladies and gentlemen,
you love him.
He's the bee's knees who
sings to please. Monty B!
What?
♪ Well, the coolest guy
In the present is me ♪
♪ And by present, I mean 1923 ♪
♪ I'm known as the
kindest cat around ♪
♪ I give money to the poor
And walk my friendly hounds ♪
♪ Burnsy, Burnsy,
Burnsy, Burns ♪
♪ That's the name
you gotta learns ♪
Are you Mr. Burns?
Mr. Burns? [chuckles]
That's my watch-winding,
ledger-loving papa.
I'm Monty B. Now let's
get this joint jumpin'.
Wow. My subconscious
is working overtime.
Why is this place called
the Little Moose Club?
That's on account of all them pint-sized
moose running around town. Look.
[moose rutting]
- Oh, my God. They're so cute.
- [moose grunts]
They look sweet, but
dang, we all hate 'em.
Their fur makes everyone sneeze.
They're the perfect height to trip
over. And they bellow off key.
[moose bellowing]
They're terrible pests
that get into everything.
Look. The town has just declared
open season on killing 'em.
- [chuckles]
- [gasps]
Edith, if we were jamming any harder
in there, we would have made marmalade.
Ha. Wow. You just said something nice.
I like this young dream version of you.
Well, you sound a little off
your onions, but I like you too.
Now let's mark our meeting by ruining
this Irish fellow's cement work.
Irish Stu gets no
respect from you.
[muttering] Hmm?
I don't normally support vandalism, but
since this isn't real, I'll cut loose.
[Lisa] Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Aw. [clamors]
- [sneezes]
- [tapper buzzing]
The sneeze woke me up.
Whoa. I had the wildest dream.
Lisa, I want you to
take these tappers home.
Write down what happens in your
dreams, so we can analyze them.
It seemed like I'd
gone back in time.
But obviously that's crazy.
Don't say that, sweetie. "Crazy"
is not a word we use in our family.
Twelve dollars for parking? What
kind of crazy office is this?
Lady, you're crazier than
Lisa and she's crazy!
To summarize, can I borrow $12?
And if you think I'm gonna
pay you back, you're crazy.
Like Lisa.
I just can't get that
dream out of my mind.
I wonder what Old Springfield
really looked like?
Gazebo, pergola, pavilion.
[gasps]
Wait. The Little Moose
Club actually existed?
Mmm. Mmm? [gasps]
It's me, or Edith.
[gasps] Or both!
You're not gonna believe it.
In that dream I had, I
went to a Jazz Age club.
And look! I was this woman.
Oh.
I think that was your
great-grandmother Edith.
She was a flapper.
But how could I have
known to dream I was her?
You must have seen her
picture in an old photo album
and it stayed in your head.
Yep. That's one of the dream laws
enforced by the dream police.
That's just a record
by Cheap Trick.
Cheap Trick is your
answer to everything.
It all just felt so real.
But, yeah… I mean, a young,
cool, jazz-singing Mr. Burns?
[sighs] I just gotta surrender
to my overactive imagination.
♪ Surrender, surrender ♪
♪ But don't give yourself away ♪
♪ Hey ♪
[stutters]
Hey. I used to be the
plow king, that's right.
- Mr. Gumble, are you okay?
- [groans]
[gasps] Oh, my God.
The picture I drew a hundred
years ago is actually there.
It wasn't a dream. I
traveled through time.
Me too. I passed out on
Tuesday and now it's Wednesday.
It's Friday.
Friday? All right, I
can sleep in tomorrow.
These tappers sent my
consciousness back in time
into the body of my ancestor,
in a Jazz Age nightclub that
used to be where Moe's is.
And then there were these tiny
moose and Mr. Burns was cool.
♪ Burnsy, Burnsy,
Burnsy, Burns ♪
Even Lisa's way of
going nuts is nerdy.
When I go crazy, it
will be on the news.
Oh, boy. I don't know.
We've got to find a
way to get her mind out
of this silly world of
magic and make-believe.
Dear God, invisible
creator of all things,
please use your superpowers
to help my daughter.
And a pizza oven.
After a decade of work,
I've finally succeeded.
- The perfect Arnold Palmer.
- [knocking on door]
Excuse me, Professor?
You're the only person I
can talk to about this.
Oh, well, please have a seat.
Uh, if you can wait six hours,
I can make you an Arnold Palmer.
Professor, I think I traveled back
through time into the body of my ancestor.
Lisa, I'm a man of science,
so I have to dismiss
that kind of tomfoolery.
But, I am also a man of science
fiction. So make like a Petri and dish.
Your experience most
resembles a quantum leap,
minus the Scott Bakula-tions.
But why is this happening?
Well, it's quite obvious.
The universe must want you to
accomplish something in the past.
Oh. Accomplish
something in the past?
I can't even get a flower
to grow in the present.
Mmm… [mutters]
In Old Springfield, did you notice
anything different or unusual?
I did. There were these
mini moose everywhere.
Mini moose? Well, to
the Internet-mobile.
Uh, clickety,
clickety, and clack.
[video narrator] The Springfield
mini moose went extinct in 1925.
That's right after the
time I traveled to.
These vulnerable little creatures were
likely the region's keystone species.
Once they were removed,
Springfield's ecosystem collapsed.
That's why our town turned
into a concrete hellscape.
If I save the moose,
I'll save Springfield.
That must be my mission.
I have to try to go back.
[slurps] Ugh.
It's a little sweet.
Oh, wonderful. Well,
fail, fail, fail.
[Lisa] Gotta save
the mini moose.
- [yells]
- [thumping]
Oh. Gotta save the
remaining mini moose.
Um, excuse me, Monty.
Edith, come in.
I was just babysitting the kids.
Orchids, that is.
You know, gardening
is a lot like jazz.
Oh! That's it. Well, the
flowers are so beautiful.
Thanks. Whenever I feel a rage coming on,
I visit my greenhouse and it calms me.
It's my gladsome place.
Nice. Mine is a stool behind the
water heater in our basement.
I read by the pilot light.
These are so unusual-looking.
Spilotantha Daphne. Named
after my dear mother,
Spilotantha.
She bred them.
As she was dying, she begged
me to take care of them.
They're all I have
left of her. [sobs]
Wow. It certainly nails
the prominent schnoz.
Yes, she was quite ugly.
My family insists that I
become a ruthless tycoon,
but I just want to sing and
grow orchids like Mother.
Monty, everyone in this town
wants to kill all the mini moose.
But if they die,
it'll ruin the town.
Will you help me save them?
Should I come to the aid
of these miniature morons?
We have a new song about the
endangered mascots of Springfield:
"The Mini Moose."
But what about the hit song "Mini
Moose Mamma, Let's Kill You Tonight"?
Okay. Wow. But this
one is even better.
[♪ band plays jazz music]
♪ Every town needs a
symbol To make its mark ♪
♪ Something keen to
set it Above the rest ♪
♪ New York's got Central Park And
St. Louis has its arch to the West ♪
The St. Louis what now?
Shoot. That hasn't
happened yet? It's coming.
♪ Paris has got
its Eiffel Tower ♪
♪ Mount Olympus has its Zeus ♪
♪ London Bridge
gives London power ♪
♪ And Springfield's
got the mini moose! ♪
I guess they do make
our town unique.
♪ Don't kill our
moosey mascots ♪
♪ Like they're some
kind of threat ♪
♪ Give them lots of cuddles
Like they're your favorite pet ♪
I'm charmed by their vacant stares
and high-pitched flatulence.
♪ So instead of kicking ♪
♪ How about going Patty
patty patty pat! ♪
♪ Patty patty patty pat! ♪
♪ Scritchy scratch,
scritchy scratch! ♪
♪ They're all convinced now
So you can stop the song! ♪
♪ We're all convinced now
So you can stop the song ♪
- Yay!
- Huzzah!
[audience cheering]
Let's go. Let's
go, little moosies.
Monty, we did it. We've
created a mini moose sanctuary.
My eyes are tearing up with emotion,
and from all the moose dander.
[all sneeze]
Professor, I think I did it.
I saved our keystone species.
So Springfield should now be
a lush, verdant wonderland.
No! What happened?
I didn't change anything. I
can never change anything.
Well, no, you did do something.
The mini moose did
not die out in 1925.
Really?
Now they died out in 1923.
No, no, no! I accelerated
their extinction?
Oh, God. I have to
go right back and...
[Marge] No one's going
right back anywhere.
[gasps] My dream
journal. You read it?
I'm a mom. Diaries
are like crack for me.
Don't take this the wrong way,
but Mom and I think you've
gone completely wackadoodle.
I haven't even gone
remotely wackadoodle.
I've gone back in time.
I have concrete proof.
No, literally, the proof
is in the concrete!
I'll show you.
We think you need a
break from the tappers.
You give those back! I need
them to save Springfield!
Oh, no, Lisa. Nothing
leaves the hive.
If I don't find
another set of tappers,
this town is doomed to be
as bad as it currently is!
Who do I know who does
more therapy than I do?
You want therapy equipment?
Therapy equipment I got.
Transcranial magnets,
vagus nerve activators,
AC and DC stimulators,
and therapy dog.
He does seem comforting,
but I need the tappers.
You can soothe me
anytime, Waggles.
- [Waggles snarls]
- Ow!
My tappers. Where
did you get them?
Mom fell asleep
eating some gummies,
so I went through her hair looking
for my burp gun, and I found these.
Thank you, Bart.
You're the only one who believes
these sent me back in time.
- [toy gun burps]
- Wrong.
When they ship you to the
funny farm, I get two rooms.
I don't know what really
killed all the mini moose,
but I'm gonna stop it.
[moose bellowing]
People of Springfield, we
are in desperate times.
This is our last stand. Our final
chance to save the mini moose!
- [moose roaring]
- Uh-oh.
No!
My Spilotantha Daphne.
No! Not even a stamen left.
Oh, no.
W-Well, we can grow more.
Surely you've saved seeds?
They only thrive in the shadow of
their mother plant. Just like me.
[sobs]
I'm so sorry.
If I can never have beauty,
neither will Springfield.
I will become a tycoon and
pave over the entire town.
And to make certain
that nothing grows,
I'll salt the earth, pepper
the oceans and cumin the sky!
No, no, no! This
can't be happening!
[Lisa sneezes]
Oh, my God, Bart.
The moose extinction
didn't ruin Springfield,
I did. I made Mr. Burns evil.
Oh, my God, Lisa.
- This thing also has a fart setting.
- [toy gun farts]
[crow squawks]
Excuse me, sir.
There's a little girl here who
refuses to let go of my leg
until she speaks to you.
Mr. Burns? We need
to talk right now.
I, or rather me as my ancestor,
performed with you at the
Little Moose Club in 1923.
And if you don't believe me,
how else could I know this?
♪ Burnsy, Burnsy, Burnsy, Burns
That's the name you gotta learns! ♪
- Edith?
- Yes. Sort of.
Look. Do you remember
the mini moose?
Remember them? I helped
send them back to hell.
I'm asking you to recall the
young man who loved flowers.
He would want you
to restore our town.
I am trying to trapdoor you,
but I can't figure out which button it
is on this new remotorized controller.
I thought I was signing
up for the softball team!
Anyway, I have never
smelled a flower in my life.
Now out!
What was I thinking?
Of course it's too late now to
change that bitter old monster.
My only chance is to
take one more shot
at convincing young Mr. Burns
not to destroy Springfield,
although the last two times I went
back, I made things way worse. Meh.
[♪ baroque harpsichord playing]
Monty, you have to believe me.
I'm from a hundred
years in the future,
where you've become bitter, mean, and
have ravaged our town's environment!
[scoffs] The future? Sounds like
someone needs a little moose oil.
Why should I do anything to keep this
knuckle-dragging palookaville beautiful,
after the wanton destruction of my
beloved Spilotantha Daphne orchids?
But wouldn't beautifying the
world make your mother proud?
Mother. Maybe it would.
Maybe it wouldn't.
Yes, that's right. It's me,
Mr. Burns from the future.
How did you get here?
I used your buzzers to zap my
old self into my young brain box.
Now, hear this, young me.
The life of a selfish
tycoon is beyond compare.
How so?
Through exploitation, war profiteering,
and owning the Las Vegas Raiders,
you will amass billions!
That does sound
possibly excellent.
Yes. You'll have a Picasso in every
bathroom, an army of loyal hounds,
and command your own Smithers.
Wealth, power, whatever a Smithers
is. It's all hard to resist.
But still, I feel a profound
darkness in my future self.
Maybe I should
find another path.
Yes! All you have to do is believe
that one person can make a difference.
Dang it!
Dad! I was just about to
save Mr. Burns's soul,
and change the course
of this town's history.
[groans]
Hmm?
I win. I convinced young
me to become old me.
And warned him not to
marry Roseanne Barr.
He's got a little more spring
in his step. That's something.
[grunts]
Uh, don't forget
your dream journal.
Oh, just throw it in the core.
Mr. Gumble, are you okay?
I left a wake-up call for 8:15.
"Edith, I left you something in the
basement of the joint where we first met."
A message from Monty B? I
gotta get into Moe's basement.
Moe, please do a favor for
a young girl hesitating
to feel even a shred
of hope, for fear of...
I don't care about your
internal struggle, okay?
Down you go.
[Monty B] My friend.
I've made my choice.
But I had one last bit of good in my
heart, so I had to purge myself of it!
I've left you a couple
remaining orchid seeds
and funding for
a beautiful park,
once you sell the priceless
Tiffany lamp I've enclosed.
- [broken glass clattering]
- Oh…
It should be safe, packed in
worthless tobacco baseball cards.
[Lisa gasps]
These are worth a fortune.
Thank you, Monty B.
Sweetie, I'm still very troubled by
all the crazy things you claim you did,
but you seem happy
right now, so all good.
It's a great garden.
Thanks, Mom. It turns out one
little girl can make a difference…
[mutters softly] As long as
she travels through time.
What a waste of time,
space and money.
I'd release the hounds on you if
this park allowed dogs off leash.
[dogs growling]
[sniffs] You're as
lovely as ever, Mother.
[jazz music playing]
♪ Mini moose mamma
Don't you know I wanna ♪
♪ Wipe you off the
face of planet Earth ♪
♪ I come from Lackawanna Where
I hear you are the fauna ♪
♪ And I'm gonna shoot you
dead For what it's worth ♪
♪ I'm gonna give a moose call
And then I'll shoot you dead ♪
♪ And up on the wall Will
go your mini moose head ♪
♪ Mini moose mamma You're
my favorite ungulate ♪
♪ Better than a llama That
I'd like to terminate ♪
♪ Mini moose mamma
Like the Oxford comma ♪
♪ I'm dying to eradicate ♪
♪ I'm gonna kill you tonight
By the silvery moon ♪
♪ I'll call you "mini moose
delight" And eat you with a spoon ♪
Shh.