The Flint Lock... whoa!
Steve!
Nerd!
Flint Lockwood!
Uh oh!
I can't believe I've never
shown you my trophy room, Sam!
Oooh, nice.
This is my Schnobel Prize.
Cool!
Aaaaah. y Schmulitzer Prize.
And this one, well
you know this one.
I got it at last
year's science fair.
Whoa whoa whoa.
Well, I mean, you didn't
win the Science Fair.
Well, sure I did.
Don't you remember?
It's where we first met.
Oh, I remember meeting you.
But I'm the one who won.
Yeah, right.
Yeah! Right.
Yeah right.
Yeah. Right.
There was a winner.
Yes.
I was the winner.
The winner's in
Lots of winning. the room.
There's a winner
...by me. in the room.
Well, why don't we
just see who's right?
Welcome students to this year's
Cannery High Science Fair!
I want to wish you all
good luck, but hey,
who are we kidding?
My son Gil is gonna win.
I won't let you down, Mr.
Mayor, Dad, Principal, sir.
No one likes a suck-up, son.
No, they don't.
Judging will commence
at the end of the week.
SO... WHO'S READY TO SCIENCE?
SCIENCE!
WHOO, SCIENCE! BRING IT ON!
BOO! What has science
ever given us?
I'm gonna win! I'm gonna win!
Sounds a bit reverb-y in here.
OH YEAH, SCIENCE!
New girl?
New girl thinks
she can come to my school
and out-nerd me?
BEHOLD! The Flint
Lockwood Enviro-Rocket,
fueled entirely by
unwanted leftovers.
Hmm. Sounds like someone needs
more congealed creamed corn.
I think we got a winner here!
Ahem. Thank you, Mayor
Principal Shelbourne.
I want to accept this science
fair award for...
Dive!
You!
You... just flew through
a cumulonimbus cloud!
I've been studying their
effects on precipitation
percentages all day.
How was it?
Cloudy.
I knew it!
Is that an organic-thrust
enviro-rocket
fueled by unwanted leftovers?
Good eye. The ham
slime coalesces
with the crusty bits of sardine.
To form a completely
efficient...
And environmentally
friendly energy source!
Exactly.
Hi. I'm Flint Lockwood.
Sam Sparks.
Sounds like you're
into science too.
Yeah! I'm
especially into weather.
Oh, speaking of which,
looks like I'm out of wind.
And I'm out of fuel!
We have so much in common.
So weird. t's true!
So much. I think we're both
about to plummet though.
Oh.
STEVE!
We are totally
going to be friends.
Whoa. I don't really do
the friendship thing.
What? But I thought...
Um, nope. Now excuse me,
I have some work to do
if I'm going to win
that science fair.
WHA? [scoffs] What?!
Well, I hate to break it to you,
but I'm going to win
that science fair.
I was born to science.
Oh wow, did that hurt?
A lot, actually.
Besides, weather isn't
really science per se.
What?!
It's kind of like a pastime,
like duck counting
or witchcraft or...
Witchcraft?!
...Maintaining an ant farm.
Of all the...
It is called meteorology.
As if your stupid invention is
going to save the world.
You know what?
I'm glad you don't do
the friendship thing.
Cause I don't do it either.
Oh, well that's fine.
Fine. Fine.
That is so fine. Fine by me.
Fine over here.
Could you argue somewhere else?
Fine!
Dad, can I talk to
you about something?
It's about a girl.
Oh, well, uh,
hm... Girl. Yes. Uuuuh.
Well, son, when a little fish
meets another little fish,
they're not, they, um, swim
around each other, you know,
and they say, "I like
this fish" so they just,
life happens, and you
know, time goes by,
and what? More fish.
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
Class, I want your full
attention. Left. Right.
Left pec. Right pec.
Left pec, left pec,
right pec, right pec.
Beat this. The Flint Lockwood
External Thought Bubbler.
Each bubble contains one
of my genius thoughts.
Prepare to be blown away.
My bum is super itchy.
Why doesn't she
want to be my friend?
I hope she doesn't
notice my itchy bum.
It's a prototype.
I'm a failure.
Allow me to present my project,
Earth's most explosive
phenomenon... THE VOLCANO!
Ooo, get out your french fries,
we got some baking soda
and vinegar over here.
Sooo impressed.
Umm, actually, it's molten lava.
You know, from the
center of the earth.
Burn!
Bring it! C'mon, mascots;
pick yourselves up!
You gotta want it more!
Nobody's winning Regionals
with that attitude.
That Sparks girl thinks she's
so smart. Well, let's see if
she can top my Flint Lockwood
Wind-Powered Sound Machine.
♪ Marching music
Not bad, if you're into lame.
Check out my Sam Sparks
Sound-powered Wind Machine!
WHAT'S THAT?!
I CAN'T HEAR YOU OVER MY
AWARD-WINNING SCIENCE PROJECT!
THE ONLY AWARD YOU'RE WINNING
IS FOR LOSING SO BADLY!
WHAT?
♪
I CAN'T HEAR YOU.
WHAT?!
WHAT?
WHAT? WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
PARDON?
MEATBALLS!
Hold on Anchor
dude! You are our only hope!
WHOA!
[screaming]. DADDY!
You're both disqualified
from this science fair
unless you FIX THIS!
Yeah, unless you fix this!
Point's been made.
It has? OK.
- Point's been made.
- Thank you.
♪
THIS IS PRETTY BAD.
I GUESS WE SHOULD...
YOU KNOW, WORK TOGETHER
AND TRY TO FIX IT.
I THOUGHT YOU DIDN'T
WANT TO BE FRIENDS.
Well, I... uh...
Hey Dad, this is that girl
I was telling you about.
Bye, Dad!
Look, if we're going to work
together, I need to know.
Why don't you like me?
It's not you, it's me. It's
just... my family moves a lot.
And every time I go to a new
place and I meet a new friend,
we end up leaving, and then I
have to say goodbye ...again.
You can write!
Just email.
You don't even know him,
honey. He's the mover.
Well, what if we agree
that if you have to move
from Swallow Falls,
I'll invent the Flint
Lockwood Memory Eraser
and it'll wipe out any
memory of our friendship.
That way you won't
have anything to miss.
You can do that?
I... uh... yeah. For a friend.
So, what do you say? Friends?
Friends. By the way, now
that we're not enemies,
your wind-powered sound
machine was kinda cool.
And your sound-powered wind
thingy wasn't half-bad either.
. That's it!
Of course!
It's such an obvious plan.
I'll bet we're thinking
the exact same thing!
♪
Pack your bags for Funky
Town, Twisty Pants!
Cuz I'm challenging
you to a dance duel.
♪
EAT SCIENCE!
You call that a twirl?
Check this out!
Hmm...
♪
We did it!
We did it.
Wait. Why are you
dressed like that?
You know... the plan.
You mean the plan where we
use the fractured reflective
surface of this giant orbiting
sphere to redirect the sun's
energy to heat up the cool
air stream at the core
of the tornado and
reverse its powerful flow?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah!
So, OK so you
weren't just having
a dance-off with
a tornado?
No.
Based on what we've just seen,
I believe there is no
doubt who should win
this year's science fair.
WOOHOO! We won. We won.
We're number one!
My son, Gil.
WHAT?!
For his work in
sardine dipping sauces.
Dippity dip, num num num,
butterscotch and squid
in my tum.
Couldn't have done it without
you, Mr. Mayor Dad, Sir.
No one likes a
suck-up, son.
No, they don't.
Hey! What about us?!
Yeah! We saved
the town.
You destroyed the town!
Plus, you worked together.
That's cheating.
Please. Please. Please.
Look, how can you
resist that face?
Oh, fine.
Here. It's for... whatever
you want to make it for.
Huh, I guess neither of us won.
What do you mean?
I clearly won.
What?! But-
And you did, too. Mayor
Principal Shelbourne
said that award could be used
for whatever we wanted.
So I'm making it our
official friendship award.
We won! We won!
We're number one!
Actually Sam, these are
typically used for number two.
Ew. You can have it.
Sardine slop.
Sardine slop or
sardine surprise.
What's the difference?
Sardine slop.
Sardine surprise!
Oh! My beautiful face!
You're just lucky
this is so delicious.
Sweet! Sardines
again! Jealous?
Do you like what you see?
Mmm, nibble nibble
nibble nibble!
Nothing? I thought
you hated sardines.
And what's with the beeps?
Of course!
Sam is a cyborg.
It all makes sense now.
Her weird square face.
Her rubbery skin.
The fact that she beats me in
an arm-wrestle so easily.
Maybe I should just ask why
your hands are giggling?
It's nothing!
Oh. Is this one of
those girl things
I'm not supposed
No. to know about?
No. Like make-up?
No. Or "sleep-overs"?
Or "feelings"?
No.
Or asking for
No. directions?
Or always asking other
girls for a hair elastic,
but it's like, why don't
you ever have one yourself?
I said it's nothing!
So it's not so hard to
see why people consider it
one of nature's most
beautiful creatures.
Is it a mind-control
pencil?
No.
Oh, it's a beard eraser.
What, No.
Is it a mind-control
beard eraser?
A shiny spaceship?
It's rhino repellent, right?
Flint Lockwood, is that
you yibber yabbering
in the middle of my
Cal-aesthetics course?
Sorry, Mr. Earl!
Friends don't keep secrets.
Which is why I'm going to show
you my weird and hideous rash.
No! OK. I will
show you. But no touchies.
OK.
Ha ha ha ha!
It's my Princess Kittymittens.
Princess Kittymittens?
What does it do?
What doesn't it do?
Princess Kittymittens!
Look at it!
Pick it up. Put it
down. Smell it out.
Lick it. Eat it!
DO NOT EAT IT!
It's cute! It's
better than friends!
than friends. If
ingested, call a doctor.
Whoa! It must be loaded up
with some awesome video games.
Nope.
Then I assume it's
equipped with its own
artificial intelligence?
Nuh-uh.
Does it interface with
orbiting satellites
to communicate with other
Princess Kittymittenses?
Nope. It's just a
Princess Kittymittens!
Ooh!
NO TOUCHIES!
Sorry. It's just... she's
like family.
I've moved so many times
and Princess Kittymittens
is the one thing that I've
always taken with me.
C'mon, just a quick game.
It's not a game! It's
a precious keepsake.
Request denied.
Just one
No. round?
C'mon! One level, that's all.
NO!
No! No. C'mon just
one, just one...
Please...
No.
I really wanna try.
I bet I could beat
the whole game!
Please!
Really?
OKAY! OKAY! YOU WIN!
Yes, but only because
you're super annoying.
But you have to be-
Super careful! Got
it! Nothing's gonna-
Uh oh.
What happened?
Ha ha ha ha.
Uh, I think I hear
my dad calling!
FLINT, it's uh, bedtime!
I can't argue with that. BYE!
Flint Lockwood,
you get back here
with my Princess Kittymittens!
Welding... nailing... taping...
Suppressing guilt...
. Aaaaah.
Behold, Princess Kittymittens!
Busted!
I know, Steve. I know.
What am I gonna do, I
gotta fix it, I gotta fi...
Sam's my best friend;
what am I gonna do,
what am I gonna do, what
am I gonna do... I got it!
Planning... tinkering...
flailing!
The Vacuu-Brush!
Flint, you're panic-inventing.
What? Me?
Panicking? Who's panicking?
Do I look like I'm panicking?
Like a bucket of
chum in a shark tank.
Flint. Flint. Flint!
It's just I borrowed Sam's
Princess Kittymittens
cause I wanted to know how it
worked but then I broke it
and now Sam's going
to hate me forever
and I don't know what to do.
Uh, why don't you just
tell her the truth?
You're right! The truth!
Aliens from another planet
kidnapped your
Princess Kittymittens!
It's a tragedy, I
know. It's... terrible.
It's the worst thing that's
ever probably happened
to you maybe, I don't
know there's a lot of...
Aliens? ALIENS? You
expect me to believe that?
A little bit. OK, so she wasn't
kidnapped.
But don't worry, Princess
Kittymittens is definitely
not completely destroyed.
Completely destroyed?! Flint,
where is my Kittymittens?!
OK, OK. But remember,
that I can still fix her.
Probably. Maybe.
But also maybe not.
Murderer! You're
a murderer! You are a...
Sam, wait...
What I... agh.
Shame. Shame. Shamity
shame shame shame shame.
Shame. Shamity shame
shame shamity shame.
Gil, I was doing the shaming.
Get out. You should be ashamed.
...and she
just kept screaming.
And calling me a
murderer! Of things,
which I didn't even
know could be murdered.
Did you tell her the truth?
Absolutely! I mean,
first I lied, obviously.
But eventually I
got to the truth.
Now she thinks we're not
friends. What do I do?
You could apologize.
First "the truth"
and now "an apology"?
You're full of
interesting ideas, Dad!
Bottoms up. Ahhh. Chum.
Sam? Can we talk? I,
well, I made you this.
Steve.
And what is that supposed to be?
It's a replacement Kittymittens!
PRETTY.
I think he looks pretty!
So, are we friends?
I'm sorry I broke your
toy. Really, I am.
Flint, Kittymittens
was very special to me.
Just imagine if I broke,
oh, I don't know, Steve.
That would be terrible!
Though I don't know how
you'd break a monkey...
Break his spirit, maybe?
Or housebreak him?
That would actually be really
great. How would I do that?
I'd have to like
get, like get a tree,
a monkey-friendly tree,
and I'd have to put it,
put a toilet by the tree
then every other day
I'd have to take
the toilet away.
And then eventually...
What were we talking about?
Flint...
- Right. Me bad, you mad.
- Hey! I know!
Because I broke
something of yours,
why don't you break
something of mine!
Then you won't be
mad at me anymore
and we can be super
best friends again!
[sigh[ That actually makes
sense. I accept.
I didn't mean for you
to break my hand... ow!
OK! You can break any
of my precious things,
just take your pick!
Mmmm... OK... that one.
No.
Not that!
That one?
Uh, no. Oh, How about that one?
Oh, that's That's not
the winner. the winner.
I don't think it is.
Oh that's the winner!
I'm thinking that.
I'm thinking not that.
Oh, that looks good.
Looks bad to me, though.
How about this? It
means A LOT to me.
I call him Prince
Paperclip and we have
lots of crazy
adventures together.
What? Nice try.
What about this?
Mr. Eureka? He's
my idea bulb!
But... I could never
get rid of him!
Fine, I'll just dry my tears
with the broken pieces
of my Princess Kittymittens.
It's a good choice.
I'm going to do it now and
then we're going to be even.
OK? So, here I go.
Wait! Let me say goodbye first!
I had so many ideas
under Mr. Eureka.
Like my lightning
proof weather balloon,
so you could track air-
to-air lightning strikes.
Oh, that was pretty cool.
Or those automatic
duck legs I made you...
for that stupid duck
parade I signed up for.
Yeah, sorry they never worked.
Or the cloud-punching machine
you said you wished you had...
So I could punch the sky
and not feel weird about it.
Yeah.
You made all those things
especially for me.
Well, I guess you can
break him now.
Awwwww... You can
keep Mr. Eureka.
[gasp] FOR REALSIES?!
YOU'RE THE BEST!
Phew. At least Mr.
Eureka didn't...
I guess I deserve that.
Flint. I don't need Princess
Kittymittens anymore...
now that I have a best friend.
Well, that's really nice.
And whoever that is,
I probably won't break it.
Probably. No promises, though.
It's you.
Oh right, me!
Of course.
Well, I definitely
won't break me!
I mean, how would you even
break a Flint Lockwood,
I don't even know how you'd...
Dah!
That's how you break
a Flint Lockwood.