The Flint Lock... whoa!
Steve!
Nerd!
Flint Lockwood!
Uh oh!
Shoo! Shoo! Get away,
you stinky rat-birds.
Oh, Sam Sparks here.
I'm with Flint Lockwood,
Swallow Falls' most
unappreciated kid inventor.
I thought we agreed
on "best inventor"?
Shhh, we're live.
Right.
Hello, Swallow Fallians!
Gather round and prepare
to be awed and amazed.
I've got every invention
to improve your life...
Three lemonades,
Flockwood. So thirsty.
Mmmm. Lemonade.
Cal's favourite.
Me too!
Extra sour.
Uh, it's not that kind of stand.
How about Laser Soap!
Demonstrating is my trusty
lab assistant, Steve!
Steve!
Hot hot hot hot hot hot!
That's right, Steve. Get
'em while they're hot!
Booo! That is awful.
I'm Baby Brent.
Whoo! Uh oh!
OK. Regrouping... how about
this: Face probe!
Rainbow dust! Sentient produce!
Or this for grooming on the go,
try the Come-Here Mirror!
Hey.
Look what you did!
You're gonna ruin this
town, Flint Lockwood!
Glad he's not my son.
That kid is strange.
Maybe I just wasn't
cut out for this.
What? Don't say
that, Flint.
You just need to find that one
invention to blow them away.
Blow them away...
That's it! Reverse dynamite.
Do your chores.
But Da-ad, I did
those months ago.
That's the thing about
chores. They're cyclical.
They come. They go. Then
hey, there they are again.
What I'm saying is...
...take out the garbage.
I'm kind of in the middle
of making the world
a better place.
Fine. Where do
you want it?
The curb.
Right! Let's see, to
the curb. Should I push?
Maybe it's more of a
pulley thing? A ramp?
Or I could dig a trench
and fill it with water
and I could float
it across on a barge
that I build out of recyclables.
Or I could build
a garbage magnet
and reverse the polarity.
You're really
over-thinking this, Flint.
That's it!
Plotting, planning, thinking.
Accepting award for
best inventor.
Thank you!
Ladies and Gentlemen
and Dad, I give you
the Flint Lockwood
Garbage Go Bye Bye,
or Fli-Lo GuhGuh-BuhBuh
for short!
No it's Guh Guh Buh Buh. Whoo!
Go Fli Guh Ba Guh Ba!
Ga-buh Ga buh. You know, it's
just weird like I don't really...
I hear the 'buh' but I don't hear the 'guh'
The emphasis is a little off though...
Like a baby! Guh
Guh Buh Buh!
Guh Buh...
Guh Guh Buh Buh!
I'll take it!
Guh Ba Ba?
Can't you just take
the garbage to the curb?
You better believe it, Dad!
You are garbage!
Whoo, did you see that?
Everyone is going to want that.
No one is gonna want that.
I want that.
Wow! Really? That's a
presale right there!
This is crazy!
Garbage.
Yee hoo!
Who is responsible for this?
Garbage.
Hey, I'm the mayor!
Sorry about that, Mr. Mayor!
Sorry about nothing!
That little gizmo of
yours is fantastic.
It's just the reason
I've been looking for
to fire the entire
sanitation department
and pocket the cash for myself.
I mean, integrity, protect the
taxpayers. Here's an idea:
can you get that
invention of yours to toss
all our town garbage
over to the dump?
Yes, sir!
I just have to re-calibrate
the feedback sensors,
amplify the power tran...
Less science-y, science,
science, and more do, do, do!
Adjusting, tweaking,
amplifying, loosening,
tightening, re-loosening,
re-tightening, twisting,
tinkering, more tinkering,
and a touch of
attitude for flavour.
Wooo weee. What is that stench?
Out of the way, Poindexter,
I've got some trash to toss.
Seriously? I've seen boogers
with better shades of green.
You. Are. Garbage!
Bye bye, baggy!
Hmm. Efficient, saucy and
completely terrifying.
Let's hear it for
Flink Lampshade!
Chore accomplished!
We'll see.
C'mon, Dad. Everyone
else likes what I did.
Sam likes what I
did. Tell him.
Oh! OK,
I like what you did.
See? Even the Mayor
likes what I did.
He gave me the key to the city.
Now I can finally
open this door.
It's just I think sometimes
there's a simpler solution
than all your buttons
and calculatin'.
It always comes back to
bite you in the caudal fin.
Huh!
A fish's behind. You
know, the pooper.
Fishing metaphors!
What ever happened
to acknowledgement,
appreciation, a parental
pat on the back...
Garbage!
Garbage! Garbage!
Hey! You are what you
eat. And you are garbage!
FLY!
FALL!
What?
Nerd bot! Clean
up in aisle 'UH OH!'
Oooooo, Brent Mchale,
baby celebrity.
Can I get your autograph?
Sure. No problem. Who
should I make it out to?
Yeah, just make it
out to my cousin.
You. Two R's. GARBAGE!
I'M TELLING MY AGENT!
Uh, Flint?
♪ Oh, I love
my money, I got money ♪
♪ and it's falling on
my head and I love it. ♪
Why hello, my main
money-making man... errr robot.
Woo! Is that a suit,
or a sausage casing?
You are garbage!
My money!
Ow!
Have no fear, citizens; your
great leader has arrived.
Oh, great leader, I
humbly bow before you!
Kick my bottom!
STEVE!
♪ Happiness...
I can't believe my dad
thinks I overthink things.
I don't overthink things! I
think out loud a lot, yeah,
but that's not the
same thing... is it?
Flint! Flint Flint
Flint Fliiiiiiiint!
Yes? Yeeeeeeeessss?
Your Guh-la-fluh-fla
has gone diva!
Oh, so now you're on team dad!
Hey, look at you, girl.
Hoo, HA! You kidding me?
You gots it goin' on
with those
trend-setting glasses...
Oh!
...And a no-fuss
ponytail.
Oh, ho.
See?
Really? Cause I just
threw this all together.
Yeah, what do you call
that, avoid-me chic?
Oh.
You are garbage!
NOW DO YOU BELIEVE ME?
I GUESS SOME OF YOUR
POINTS ARE VALID.
You heard our Monkey Overlord;
he wants us to peel away
all our worldly possessions.
I'll go first.
C'mon, don't be
intimidated by my freedom;
your freedom is just as good.
Hello?
Anyone?
Dad was right. There's
definitely an easier way
to take out the garbage.
Hey! What's with the long face?
Aaaah, sorry, it's
always that way.
You. Are. Garbage!
Think, Flint, think! I
could karate slap it.
I could, I could start
a store for robots only
and then when he comes in
to buy something I'll say,
"Hey, we're not open today"
and then I'll call the
police! For trespassing.
FLINT! Seriously.
Don't overthink it.
Hey, excuse me, mister,
the 70's called.
They want their moustache back!
My mother gave me
this moustache.
Daaad!
That's it! Your reign
of cleanliness is over!
Gripping.
Struggling. Stretching.
Look at you. Failing.
Stinking. Losing. Laming.
Before that. ay? Laming?
Losing?
No.
StiNo.ng?
FaiNo.g?
Look at you?
That's it!
The Come-Here Mirror!
Look at me!
Shoddy workmanship.
Cheap plastic parts. Offshore
electronics.
You... Are... GARBAGE.
♪
And now, a sacrificial gift
for our monkey overlord.
This town is so weird.
Garbage!
GARBAGE! GARBAGE! GARBAGE!
Hey! Ow!
Well, it looks like
everything is back to normal.
I proclaim myself
the Mayor once again.
I'm the mayorest!
A merry moda-mooda-mada-meeda
bud up doodle op deedle
op doodle up mayor!
Sorry, Dad. You were
right from the get-go.
I should have just
taken out the garbage
instead of building a super
cool, awesome killer robot.
Maybe we could start with a
simpler chore. Like... dishes.
Hmm, dishes.
I'LL DO IT YOUR WAY
NEXT TIME. I PROMISE!
Just run.
And scream?
Good thinking, son.