The Flint Lock... whoa!
Steve!
Nerd!
Flint Lockwood!
Uh oh!
♪ There's a story
told of a fish so old ♪
♪ And his name was
Johnny Sardine ♪
♪ He was a magic fish
If you made a wish ♪
♪ He'd grant it and
all your dreams. ♪
♪ Johnny!
♪ Johnny Sardine!
Happy Birthday, Johnny Sardine!
There's no way that
sardine is 50 years old!
I mean look at him,
that's ridiculous.
I know. He looks
great for his age.
And after all these years.
Johnny Sardine in
the Mod 60s, the 70s
when he discovered rock and
roll, the power-suit 80s,
the slacker 90s.
Always super famous.
Always granting wishes.
It makes no sense. Unless...
granting wishes
is a form of energy
represented by "E"
over T for Time divided
by the rate of aging...
Nope, no sense.
Move it! Average
people back off. Uh oh!
Hey Sam. It's me,
Baby Brent. Boom!
Yo, Fishery-dude!
I wish my face could even be
more impossibly beautiful
than it already is. Just do it.
Oh, look at that jaw!
It's like it's 3D.
Thanks, Jimmy Sardinelli.
Uh oh! BB out.
Wow.
And if you think that's cool.
I don't. I do not.
There was this one time
I wished for a pony
and when I got home...
Flint, there's a pony on TV.
LOOK, IT'S A PONY!
THERE'S A PONY ON TV!
AH, IT'S LIKE A
LITTLE HORSE!
Whoa.
Flint Lockwood, I won't have
you threatening Swallow Falls'
most beloved wish-granting fish
with your jumpy up and
downy nincompoopery.
Morning Mr. Earl.
You're crushing my lungs.
Oh, Great Johnny Sardine.
Give me a sign that
my precious son, Cal,
loves his daddy even half as
much as his daddy loves him.
Woohoo! You did it
again, Johnny Sardine.
You did it again. Happy
Birthday. Whoo hoo hoo!
Give it a go.
Oh fine. But only to
prove how lame this is.
How 'bout an ice cream.
Wha?! How.
Did that happen?
That's the power
of Johnny Sardine!
That'll be two bucks, kid.
- A wish-granting fish.
- . Who knew?
My turn. Let's
see... that's it!
Ah! I killed
Johnny Sardine!
C'mon, Flint, it's
a sardine, right?
How much trouble can
we possibly get into?
Hey-hey-hey! As the Mayor
of Swallow Falls...
Sorry, Dad.
I have an announcement to make.
It's Johnny Sardine's
50th birthday!
So if anything
happens to him today,
that person or persons are in
BIG TROUBLE! HUGE TROUBLE!
So where's the birthday boy?
C'mere you little finny friend.
Where are you hiding?
He's uh...
He's teleported to
another dimension!
He got a really
lucrative job offer...
...to that drug store...
...drug store
over... under the water...
...under the bridge...
Good thing I'm not
listening to either of you.
Yoo-hoo, Johnny!
I have an idea, Sam.
Great, we tell Mayor Shelbourne
that it was all an accident?
No, I'll invent Johnny
Sardine back to life!
TO THE LAB! But
first... MAYOR DISTRACTION!
Fine.
Yes I do.
Want an ice cream?
I do, I do want some ice cream! Mmmm.
Little ice cream, little ice cream...
So distractingly delicious.
I wasn't finished!
♪ HE WAS A MIGHTY
FISH, BUT WAS PENNY SQUISHED, ♪
♪ AND FLAT WAS JOHNNY SARDINE.
♪ HE WAS ONCE A SWIMMER BUT
NOW LOOKS LIKE DINNER, ♪
♪ GOTTA SAVE THAT
JOHNNY SARDINE. ♪
Dr. Flint, we
lost him.
OVER! OVER!
Not yet, Lab Assistant Steve.
It's not over till
the fat fish fries.
Still looking very dead.
Inflating.
Deflating.
And... CLEAR!
Still dead.
Pickling.
Flambéing!
Nope.
And... CLEAR!
He gone.
Clear harder!
Begging! Please come back,
oh wish-granting sardine.
Johnny, it's me
Flint, we met earlier.
JOHNNY!
It's about time! Wah!
Why don't we just tell
the Mayor the truth?
We can't tell anyone. Johnny
Sardine was a fish hero.
Songs were written about him.
Not good ones, but songs!
Hey, come on. They
can't all be hits.
He's not smelling so fresh.
I know. I just
wish, I wish...
That's it! I'll just wish Johnny
Sardine back to normal.
I wish for Johnny Sardine
to be good as new.
YOU'RE THE ONE
RESPONSIBLE FOR THIS!
Responsible for
these shiny floors?
Take a look at those hammies.
Even my pecs are shimmering
Whoa, Earl, put those pecs
away before you hurt someone.
Again?
I can't believe anyone buys
this oldest fish
malarkey anyway.
Now to collect
all those pennies.
I'm a wish-destroyer.
A dream-crusher.
A hope-squashing
fish-squisher.
Relax. They don't
even know it's us.
I'M GONNA LOCK YOU UP!
Lock you up, good and tight
so no one can steal you!
Such a cute little
bike. Look at that bell.
Bing bing bing bing!
♪ THEY WERE OUTLAWS
ON THE RUN. ♪
♪ CAUSE THE DIRTY
DEED WAS DONE. ♪
♪ THEY DONE KILLED JOHNNY.
♪ JOHNNY SARDINE
Mmmm, that's some nice scales.
Dad! I'm leaving town!
Your son is a nothing
but a sardine-killer.
If anyone asks, I loved
that Johnny Sardine
like he was my slimey bro. I
tried to save him, Dad. I tried.
Uhm... uhm... Gone Fishing.
THIS IS CRIMINAL!
Criminal how tasty your ice
cream is.
I only wish my whole body was
a tongue so I could roll up
in this here ice cream and
taste it all over.
I know a guy who can
make that happen.
It's invasive; it's expensive;
and you will regret it.
We can't stay in
Swallow Falls anymore.
We have to put
as much distance between us
and the scene of the
crime as possible.
OK, this'll be fun.
Yeah. We'll get
new identities.
Oh, we'll get really
convincing wigs.
We'll change our voices.
Invent new laughs.
And we'll need cool aliases.
Like, I'll be Rocket Johnson,
and you can be Swamp Worm.
What, no! I don't
wanna be Swamp Worm.
I want to be Rainbow
Mist, Queen of the Clouds.
No no, it's gotta be
tougher, like, Stingray,
or Cobra Strike.
Or Spruce Willis.
I don't wanna be that.
I don't wanna be Spruce
Willis; that's silly.
Actually I think
I'll be Cobra Strike.
Wait, do you hear something?
MEATBALLS!
Who's ready to Party?
Uh oh! They're hot
and ready, watch it!
My mouth is willing and open...
They're hot little
nuggets; have some!
They've been in
here all day. Whoo!
Whoo!
This town is so weird.
C'mon Sam, JUMP!
Agh!
What can I say about Johnny
Sardine? . Not much.
But today we celebrate his
50th birthday with respect.
By respect, I mean,
money in the fountain.
Roll in the cake!
2 bucks a slice.
You wanna use a fork,
that's another dollar.
If you wanna use a
spoon, that's 50 cents.
But you have to
buy a fork with it.
Flint Lockwood, and new girl
whose name I can never remember!
Sitting in a cake is pure shenaniganism.
It's Sam.
Intolerable by law!
FOR SHAMEITY SHAME SHAME!
Drop and give me twenty!
Flint, we have to
tell the truth!
You're right, Sam. Our
days on the lam are over.
No more ruthless renegades
on the run from old man law.
What? We didn't
really run.
We were children
of the universe. What?
...and now we must return.
Thank you, we got it.
Mayor Shelbourne,
fellow Swallow Fallians.
I'm afraid we killed...
Stop the press!
That is not Johnny Sardine.
Boo!
Outrageous!
Lies! What's-her-name lies!
The foreign one lies!
No, Sam's right. It's a
Johnny Sardine miracle!
My wish came true!
He's good as new!
But we totally killed him. And
that fish has a moustache.
Oh Sam, don't you see? Johnny
Sardine isn't about facts,
or truth, or even facial hair.
He's about hope, and
wonder, and believing
something good can happen.
Who doesn't want that?
The kid's right. Hey, if you
want to cynically believe
that I replace Johnny
Sardine every day,
is that what you're
trying to tell me?
Is that what's happening now?
Then you just go right ahead.
I mean, here's one
for next Monday.
And how about this one
for Thursday?
Please. Like I'd do that.
Now it's got an eye
patch and an afro.
Looking good, little fishy.
This town is so weird.
Happy Birthday, Johnny Sardine!
♪AND THAT'S THE
BALLAD OF JOHNNY SARDINE ♪