(Mulder) "At times I almost dream
I too have spent a life the sages' way,
And tread once more familiar paths.
Perchance I perished
in an arrogant self-reliance an age ago;
And in that act, a prayer
for one more chance went up so earnest,
So instinct with better light let in by death,
That life was blotted out, not so completely
But scattered wrecks enough of it
to remain dim memories,
As now,
When seems once more
The goal in sight again."
(man) Federal agents! We are armed!
Let's go! Move, move, move!
Keep down on the ground!
We have warrants to search
for illegal firearms!
We have warrants
for the arrest of Vernon Warren...
...also known as Vernon Ephesian.
Move it, move it!
Come on, come on, let's go!
Move, move, move!
(agents yelling)
Someone tipped Ephesian off.
He's somewhere on the compound.
- (Scully) Ephesian?
- No. We've covered 90% of the compound.
- (Scully) We have to find him.
- No sign of weapons.
- They've hid them somewhere.
- Where haven't we covered?
We could check the machine shop again.
Maybe they've got trap doors.
Mulder. Mulder!
Tear it apart.
Mulder? Mulder, where are you going?
Intelligence reported
no hiding places beyond the yard.
Did you see someone?
(woman's voice)
"I am he that liveth, and was dead."
"And, behold...
...I am alive for evermore."
(voice continues)
(woman praying)
- (woman continues praying)
- FBI!
" No!
" (gasps)
It's OK. It's OK.
(man) Bureau of Alcohol,
Tobacco and Firearms transmission
received 0230 hours...
...5 November '96, Apison, Tennessee.
Confirmed telephone trace
from within Seven Stars compound.
BATF. This is Agent Kiley.
(man 2) OK, I'm not gonna talk long.
I can't even believe I'm doing this.
OK, Vernon - he's got a lot of good ideas.
He's right about a lot of things...
...but he's doin' stuff to kids now that...
It ain't good.
I'm telling you, it is not why I signed on.
(Kiley) OK, OK, easy.
- Can you tell me your name, sir?
- Call me Sidney.
Vernon - he's hurtin' little kids
around here bad. It ain't right.
And the guns, my God, you could
beat the whole Korean army here.
Oh, God, I can't talk no more. I got...
(dialling tone)
This call capped off a BATF investigation...
...of the Temple of the Seven Stars
led by Vernon Ephesian.
That call convinced the Attorney General
to give the OK for our raid.
ATF intelligence reports were weak.
Our man, Spooky, found Ephesian
in a bunker ATF didn't even know was there.
- How did you know that?
- (men arguing)
Knock it off!
The reports are valid. Illegal activities
were going on at that compound.
They were alerted in time
to hide the evidence.
Ephesian and his wives are held on charges
of possession of dangerous chemicals.
Their attorneys will be
pushing for a quick arraignment.
They'll be out of here in less than 24 hours
if we cannot charge them.
Agents on site will continue to search
for evidence of illegal firearms.
And even more critical,
find the informant "Sidney".
If they found out that he tipped us,
it's likely we're looking for a murderer.
All right, go.
Agent Mulder, Agent Scully...
...you were assigned to this operation to
investigate Ephesian's paranormal abilities:
...channelling, astral projection.
He's a paranoid charismatic sociopath,
obsessed with the Book of Revelation.
He will use his Biblical knowledge to get
anything he wants from his followers.
Ephesian had six women on the verge
of suicide. You witnessed it.
If the temple members are released...
...any Federal investigation
will ignite Ephesian's paranoia...
...to such a degree that we won't have
another Waco on our hands.
We'll have Jonestown.
I knew you were coming.
I've known for nine centuries.
It was written
in the Revelation of Jesus Christ.
"Behold, ...
...the devil shall cast some of thee
into prison that you may be tried."
"You'll have tribulation ten days."
"Be thou faithful unto death,
and I'll give thee a crown of life."
But that message
was to the church at Smyrna.
Your temple is the reincarnation
of the church at Ephesia.
Mine is the Temple of the Seven Stars.
All seven churches receiving the Revelation.
And the members are not
a reincarnation of the church.
Are you?
Oh, yes. I was present
to hear Apostle John Mark
deliver his message of the Apocalypse.
Vernon, if Sidney was unfaithful,
did he receive a crown of life?
There are no members of the Temple
named Sidney.
But I know you don't believe.
I don't care if you think that
I'm Jim Jones or David Koresh.
I don't need you to believe or even like me.
But just for a moment, I'd like you
to put aside your investigation...
...for your own souls.
It is vital that you understand
that very, very soon...
...all unfaithfuls, all disbelievers, all beasts -
...if that means me or...
...this "Sidney"... or...
--YOu _
...all will be destroyed by God's mighty men.
It is what has been told by God will happen.
It is what has been told by God we must do.
Do this, and the Lord
shall preserve you from all evil.
He will preserve your soul.
The Lord will preserve your going out...
...and your coming in.
(Scully) Skinner said no one else
has come up with anything.
They've started to release
members of the Temple.
The compound
remains under Federal control, though.
Time is flying.
We've got six wives to question.
My estimate is 12 more hours of fire and
brimstone, and not a second about Sidney.
Let's start with her.
My name is Melissa Riedel Ephesian. I'm 25.
Melissa, do you understand
your right to have an attorney
present at this questioning?
It's OK.
Where are you from?
I don't know.
What about your family?
Where do they live?
My real family's here.
How long have you lived there?
A year.
How long have you been married
to Ephesian?
A year.
Does it bother you he has other wives?
"And on that day, seven women
shall take hold of one man, saying...
...we shall eat our own bread,
we shall wear our own apparel...
...only let us be called by thy name
to take away our reproach."
That's quite a faith you have in Vernon.
I'd have a tough time if my husband
had so many children with other women.
Do you have a child by Vernon?
Someday.
Vernon has to wait until God tells him when
the right soul is ready to be reincarnated.
That's why Vernon's children are
the most sacred members of the Temple.
We were told
that Vernon's been hurting the children.
Have you ever witnessed any child abuse
at the temple, Melissa?
(man's voice) I don't know
where you're gettin' that from.
I saw a coupla things.
It could have been anything, right?
Melissa?
No. I don't know nobody called that.
- Sidney?
- What is this? The McCarthy hearings?
No, no... Don't...
Don't know anybody by that name. No.
I saw a coupla things.
It could have been anything, right?
Sidney, who is the President
of the United States right now?
Who's the President of the United States?
What kind of dumb question is that?
That is a stupid question. Harry Truman.
Sidney is a past life
just because she mentioned Joe McCarthy?
It's not just that.
Somehow I just knew.
(door opens)
Ephesian and his wives
get arraigned tomorrow.
That's 15 hours to come up with something.
"Come up with something"?
We found Sidney.
Melissa Riedel's vocal pattern
matches the ATF Sidney call.
Melissa Riedel is not co-operating.
But there is a personality within her
that wants to.
We need a catalyst. I suggest
we take her back to the compound.
Maybe without Ephesian there,
it will enable Melissa to talk,
or a personality inside her.
Agent Scully,
could this be a staged diversion?
- I thought multiple personalities were rare.
- They're extremely rare.
In fact, many in the psychiatric community
do not believe they exist.
What we witnessed meets the criteria
established in the DSM-IV.
Two or more distinct personality states
that recurrently take control
over behaviour...
...including the protector identity, Sidney.
The inability to recall personal information.
She couldn't recall her home town.
Transitions are usually a matter of seconds
and are often caused
by psychosocial stress.
Sidney appeared when we mentioned
that children had been abused.
- But you remain unconvinced?
- I believe the disorder exists...
...but I would have to know more.
If Melissa has multiple personalities, would
her... his testimony even be admissible?
Precedents have established that
dissociative personalities are responsible.
But we are responsible for Melissa Riedel.
We are responsible for
the potential loss of 50 lives.
Do it.
You didn't tell Skinner
what you really believe.
That Melissa Riedel is being invaded
by her past-life incarnations.
- He wouldn't believe me.
- You don't feel responsible for the 50 lives...
...or Melissa Riedel.
You are only responsible
to yourself, Mulder.
(Mulder) You're safe with us, Melissa.
The murderer's not here.
(Scully) We know that events occurred here
that may be painful.
You may not wanna talk about them,
you may be afraid to remember.
But to help the others,
to help the children and to help yourself...
...we're here with you to listen...
to Melissa, to Sidney...
...to whoever may need to talk.
Melissa?
Why you calling me that?
- What should I call you?
- Lily.
Lily... were any of your friends
hurt in this room?
What?
Can you do this?
Melissa... Lily...
It's OK to tell me.
(Sidney) Look, leave the kid alone. Hear me?
She doesn't wanna talk. Right? No way.
I'm sending her home.
Sidney, you can all go home.
You can all be safe...
...if you tell us where they hid the guns.
What's wrong?
(Southern accent) The weapons were placed
in the bunker they'd built the night before.
That's why they weren't on the ATF reports.
The Federals would arrive in the morning,
just before the sun.
Realising the government's
might and number...
...most believed they, indeed,
would never again...
...see the light of day...
...just as they had watched their brothers die
days before on Missionary Ridge.
We had received word of General Cleburne's
retreat from the Union army.
As a nurse, I had been ordered from
Hamilton County to meet the troops, but...
...in actuality, I was searching for him...
...knowing that he would attempt
to remain in Tennessee...
...rather than retreat to Dalton.
I found him here...
...amongst the others who had been lost...
...as General Thomas pushed through
the Confederate line.
The Federal troops would appear
from that direction.
Rather than retreat any further,
they fought them...
...hidin' us in the bunker.
Inside, I could...
...smell the smoke...
...hear the rifles...
...feel the bodies as they dropped
onto the ground above.
Every last one.
26th November...
...1863.
I was here...
...as were you.
This is the field where I watched you die.
(Scully) Who are you calling?
I want a therapist trained in hypnosis
to be at the command centre.
Because hypnosis is used
to treat dissociative identities...
...to bring forth a patient's
various personalities?
She wants to talk, Scully.
It's a matter of getting it out of her.
No, it's about regressing her to a past life.
Don't do this to her, Mulder. This poor
woman's mind, her life is in shreds.
Just being married to Ephesian indicates
she is susceptible to suggestion.
You were there, Scully!
You saw it. You heard it.
Why can't you feel it?
How could I know about a bunker
in a field I've never been in?
And why is it that Vernon Ephesian is
reported by you a paranoid sociopath...
...because he believes
he lived 100 years ago...
...and you're not, even though you believe
you died in that field?
(therapist) I'm talking to Melissa.
In the last year,
at the Temple of the Seven Stars...
...is there anything that happened that
you thought was wrong, that hurt you?
Yes.
There was a...
...woman who came to the temple.
She and her son
had been living on the streets.
What was her name?
Elizabeth.
Her son was Scott.
Vernon took a liking to the boy.
He said that he was a prophet returning.
He took the boy away from his mother.
Took him away? How?
Vernon's children are the grandchildren
of God, kept separate from the others.
The mother's heart was broken.
She was afraid.
The Mighty Men...
Late... night...
...Liz sneaks in to see Scott.
Oh, he was happy-
She brings him a butterfinger
she stole from the kitchen.
Vernon... Vernon...
...Vernon catches them.
The Mighty Men...
...they pull her away, and beat her...
...in front of her son.
The boy... "No, no, Mom!"
(crying)
Vernon... Vernon...
...Vernon pulls him by...
...Vernon pulls him by his hair...
...pulls down his pyjamas, and hit him.
"You're not a child of God."
"Garbage", he calls him.
He told him to sleep in the trash...
...with the rats.
The mother... the mother cries...
...but Vernon beats him...
...in front of her.
(whimpering) Oh! Oh! No, no, no!
(Sidney) Lookit!
Brilliant, brilliant, brilliant move!
What d'you wanna know? Just... just...
Leave Melissa alone. She doesn't need to
go through that any more.
- Where are the guns?
- The b-bunkers. Yeah.
The Civil War bunkers. Vernon... Vernon...
Vernon and his goons know, but I don't.
Maybe there's a map
of the battlefield in the records.
You know how to find the other bunkers.
Mulder...
Melissa.
It's me, Melissa.
I want you to go back...
...back to the field.
(Sobs)
Oh!
(Southern accent)
Your eyes may have changed shade...
...but it cannot colour the soul behind them.
We have come together
in this life, this time...
...only to meet in passing.
It is so heartbreaking to wait.
I miss you.
Mulder, this is a product of her illness.
She couldn't answer the question on the
battlefield. She gave us no specific names...
...no information to prove her validity.
There is nothing we can use
to prove this is the truth.
There's one way.
Ephesian's arraignment is in two hours.
There is no time to be doing this.
Wouldn't you, Scully?
Wouldn't anybody?
(therapist) I want you to go into your past,
beyond your life as Fox Mulder.
What do you see?
Ghetto streets.
Shattered glass.
Bodies of the dead.
I'm a woman...
...a Jewish woman.
Poland.
My son is with me.
- He is Samantha.
- (therapist) Samantha?
I thought Samantha was your sister.
In this life...
...she is my son.
I see my father.
He's dead in the street.
He is Scully.
But now... He's gone on now.
They're waiting for us.
Souls...
...come back together.
Different, ...
...but always together...
...again and again...
...to learn.
I can't go to my father.
(sighs)
Gestapo is standing next to him.
An officer.
He is Cancer Man.
Evil returns as evil.
But love...
...love...
...souls mate... eternal.
My... husband...
...is taken away from me...
...to the camps.
He is Melissa.
We're always taken away.
I'm rising.
I'm rising now.
I'm rising now...
...high above...
...my body...
...above the field.
My face is bloody.
Near the bunker.
The Federals are gone.
My sergeant is also dead.
He is Scully.
Sarah holds me.
She is sad.
She is Melissa.
She lives...
...near the battle.
Hamilton County.
Her name is Kavanaugh...
Sarah Kavanaugh.
And my name...
...is Sullivan Biddle.
She doesn't know.
She doesn't know...
...that I'm waiting for her...
...that we will live again.
We will live again.
Oh, my soul is tired.
Mulder, it's Scully.
Do you see any bunkers in the field?
My soul is tired.
I wanna rest.
(Scully) Ephesian's being taken down
to his arraignment.
He and Melissa
are going to be released soon.
Dana... if, um...
...early in the four years
we've been working together...
...an event occurred that suggested
or somebody told you that...
...we'd been friends together...
...in other lifetimes... always...
...would it have changed some of the ways
we looked at one another?
Even if I knew for certain...
...I wouldn't change a day.
Well, maybe that "Flukeman" thing.
I could have lived without that just fine.
(Sarah) We have come together
in this life, this time...
...only to meet in passing.
It is so heartbreaking to wait.
(Sarah sighing)
I miss you.
- I don't believe in it.
- Why?
Those tapes are saying we chose
the lives we live before we're born...
...and who we live with.
It's a nice idea.
It's a beautiful idea.
I wanna believe.
And if I knew it were true,
I'd want to start over.
I'd want to end this pointless life.
Sarah...
...if it were true...
...no life would be pointless.
(door opens)
Melissa...
...it's time to leave.
I've reported to investigators
the possible existence of other bunkers.
The field is not the property of the Seven
Stars, so the BATF is continuing to search.
(girl) Mommy! They're home!
The Attorney General is furious as is.
We won't get a go-ahead
for a second move on the compound.
Ephesian's followers believe that the FBI
and the ATF are the devil's army...
...prophesied in Revelations 12:17
to make war on the seed...
...keeping God's commandments
and the testimony of Jesus Christ.
Revelations says Christian faith
defeats that army.
You're saying he'll attack the ATF agents,
believing, as prophesied, he'll win?
I would be saying that if I thought
he believed in Revelations in its entirety.
- But he hid the weapons.
- He knew he couldn't defeat us.
If he doesn't believe
he can defeat that army...
...he may think by denying himself and his
followers to the devil... You understand?...
...he will achieve for them
the reward of life forevermore.
Our worst fears will be realised.
All members to worship.
The Lord shall preserve you from all
your evils. He shall preserve your soul.
All members to worship. The Lord
shall preserve you from all your evil.
He shall preserve your soul.
"Marvel not, my brethren,
that the world hates you."
"We know we've passed from death into life
because we love the brethren."
I will not remove our people.
We're close to finding the weapons.
All I want is a cooling-off period.
Ephesian's gathered all members
in the worship hall.
A parabolic mike we have aimed
at the compound just picked this up.
(Ephesian) "Marvel not, my brethren,
that the world hates you."
(door latched)
"We know we've passed from death into life
because we love the brethren."
"Hereby perceive we the love of God
because he laid down his life for us."
The temple began running
an interference frequency.
First Epistle of John:
"He laid down his life for us, and we ought
to lay down our lives for the brethren."
OK, Mulder.
(Ephesian) "Blessed are they
that do his commandments...
...that they may have the right
to the tree of life."
My little children...
...let us not love in word, neither in tongue...
...but in deed and truth.
And hereby, we know that we are the truth.
We shall endure.
(agent) Man down! Man down!
- Get him out of there!
- Cease fire!
Hold your fire! Hold your fire!
- Is there contact with the temple?
- If you call that "contact".
He should be transported right away.
"And enter in through the gates
into the city!"
"For without are dogs...
...and sorcerers...
...and whoremongers...
...and murderers, idolaters."
"Whomsoever...
...loveth and maketh a lie."
(Scully) Mulder, no!
You're dead!
(Sobs)
"Behold, ...
...I am alive for evermore."
(Mulder) "At times I almost dream
I too have spent a life the sages' way,
And tread once more familiar paths.
Perchance I perished
in an arrogant self-reliance an age ago;
And in that act, a prayer
for one more chance went up so earnest,
So instinct with better light let in by death,
That life was blotted out not so completely
But scattered wrecks,
enough of it to remain dim memories,
As now,
When seems once more
The goal in sight again."
Subtitles by Visiontext
(Child) I made this!