(footsteps)
(squeaking)
(fizzling sound)
(siren blaring in distance)
(Scully) Not everything is a conspiracy.
You're shaking.
(Mulder) One at a time. What's going on?
- (man) Frohike's close.
- Don't use my name!
Now I'll have to kill you!
(man) Langley and I
did three sweeps with the CPM-700.
(Frohike) The CPM-700 is a piece of crap!
(man) The acoustic correlator
is reading passive sounds.
(Mulder) I still don't know
what the hell is wrong!
No one would kill you, Frohike.
You're a puppy dog.
(man 2) I don't say any more until the
CSM-25 counter measure filter is activated.
(garbled voices)
(Static)
(man) Nothing can cut through the CSM-25.
(Scully) OK, OK.
Now tell us what you're so close to.
(Frohike) Not a what, a who.
If you find the starting point and follow it,
not even secrets
of the darkest of men are safe.
(Mulder) Cancer Man?
- What did you find?
- (Frohike) Possibly everything.
Maybe his background, who he is,
and who he wants to be.
August 20th, 1940, Mexico City.
A Stalinist agent assassinated
Leon Trotsky with an ice pick.
At that same moment,
a thousand miles north,
in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, he appears.
The father was
an ardent Communist activist.
During the Nazi-Soviet pact,
he kept the NKVD informed...
...on American plans to enter World War ll.
He was executed
under the Espionage Act of 1917...
...before his boy could walk.
The mother, a cigarette smoker,
died of lung cancer...
...before her son uttered his first word.
With no family,
he became a ward of the state...
...sent to various orphanages
in the Midwest.
Didn't make friends.
Spent all his time reading - alone.
And then... he appears to have vanished...
...until a year and a half after the Bay of Pigs.
(man) Premier Khrushchev, we want you!
(troops) Premier Khrushchev, we want you!
We're gonna kick your rang-a-dang-doo!
Fidel Castro, we want you!
Mother Russia...
(man) I wanna see that
when you're done with it.
Why don't you go see the movie?
I'd rather read the worst novel ever written
than sit through the best movie ever made.
Captain, sir!
General Francis requests
you report to his office ASAP, sir!
My one-year-old just said his first word.
- What was the word?
- JFK.
Catch ya later, Mulder.
- (buzzer)
- (man) He's here, sir.
Send him in.
You wish to see me, sir?
Have a seat, Captain.
Captain, have you ever seen these two men,
met the general, or myself?
No, sir.
In January, 1961,
did you aid Congo president Kasavuba...
...in the arrest and assassination
of Patrice Lumumba?
No, sir.
Did you train Cuban nationals
during Operation Zapata...
...also known as The Bay Of Pigs?
I'm sorry, I'm unaware of
any such operation.
On May 31st,1961...
...did you aid Dominican locals
in the assassination of Rafael Trujillo?
No, sir.
Your father was a convicted spy
for the Soviet Union.
Executed in a Louisiana electric chair,
was he not?
My only regret, sir, is I was too young
to throw the switch myself.
At ease, Captain. Your father's actions
were totally out of your control.
Each of us in this room understands
a life eviscerated by the actions of another.
Cigarette?
No, thank you, sir. I never touch 'em.
You see, most people seek to control life's
events in order to secure a more positive...
...productive and free existence.
Often, however, the objectives of others
conflict with our objectives.
Viva la Iibertad.
Now, most people -
common people, really -
...can barely manage to control
their own self-centred,, myopic existence.
They command lawyers
armed with paper weapons...
...attacking with spiteful, vengeful,
cowardly litigation.
Others...
...operate within elephantine bureaucracies.
And then, Captain...
...there are extraordinary men.
Those who must identify, comprehend
and ultimately shoulder the responsibility...
...for not only their own existence...
...but their country's,
and the world's as well.
Your father, Captain, believed his country
should look to
another form of government...
...and he took control of that belief.
So, in that respect...
...we view him as an extraordinary man.
And we believe...
...we know, Captain,
that it runs in the family.
Now, don't misunderstand.
Your father should have been executed.
Communism is the most heinous
personification of evil...
...mankind has ever confronted.
And it is, in part, the reason
that you are before us here today.
You must understand everything I'm about
to say is classified "compartmentalised."
So intensely
that if you accept this assignment...
...and successfully execute it, you will
no longer be an officer of the US army...
...nor will any record exist of your service.
The assignment...
...is the assassination
of an American civilian, aged 46...
...former naval PT boat commander.
Married, father of two.
Last week this country was brought
to the brink of nuclear annihilation.
A situation which never would have arisen
had the individual, as commander in chief...
...provided an umbrella of air support
during the invasion at Bahia de Cochinos.
Is there a cover story?
Tell 'em it was done
by men from outer space.
We've found and are setting up a patsy.
Where?
You shouldn't smoke those, Lee.
I'm reading studies
that say they can kill you.
Well...
...Mr Hunt...
...sir...
...I've, uh, heard about those reports and...
...they are no doubt correct.
You'll have a good view
of the president today.
I like the president's family.
They're interesting people.
However, I have my own views
on the president's national policy.
I'll probably just eat lunch.
I'm going to the movies
at the Texas Theatre.
It's only 90 cents.
I love the movies.
I brought the curtain rods, Lee.
I bought some
just like this back in March.
You did?
Or AJ Hidell?
Well, Mr Hunt,
Fidel's defenders have to be careful.
Yes, we do.
I've informed our fellow defender that you'll
hide the curtain rods on the 6th floor...
...of the book depository,
behind the cartons against the back wall.
The Cuban visa?
Once I've been notified the rods
have been removed from the depository...
...the visa and the money for your trip
will be in your room.
Take a bus.
I left all my money with my wife.
That's all I've got: 13 and change.
You better get going, Lee. You wouldn't
want to miss your ride to work.
(shuffling sound)
Oh! Good morning, Lee.
Starting work right on time.
Yes, sir.
The president should be driving past any
minute. Everyone's down on the 5th floor.
Where's Lee? Does he wanna come?
(chattering)
(cheering)
(man on radio) The president's car
is now turning onto Elm Street.
(sighs)
I was on the Stemmons freeway earlier...
...and it was jam-packed with spectators
waiting to see the president.
People are really starting to crowd in.
(buzzing sound)
The motorcade
is heading down Elm Street now...
...passing the Texas School Book Depository.
(gunshot)
(people screaming)
I can't quite see from here. Something
has happened on the motorcade route.
Does anyone know what happened?
Is there any information?
(man) Upstairs!
- Do you know this man?
- Yes, he works for me.
Let's go)!
(people shouting)
(sirens blaring, people shouting)
(man on radio) The president
of the United States is dead.
It is official now. President Kennedy is dead.
No! No! No, sir!
I won't be a patsy.
(police radio)
...should be considered dangerous,
and use caution approaching.
Afternoon.
(radio continues)
I wish to see
some form of identification, sir.
Now easy there, partner.
I just wanna talk a minute.
If I don't see valid credentials,
I'm gonna assume you're with them.
Them? What do you mean, partner?
(gunshots)
How about a cigarette?
Thank you.
You know, Keiffer knocked out a bunker.
All by himself, too.
(soldier 2) More guts than me.
All I did was pick up the spoils.
(soldier 1) But he's really gone.
After Connors and Thurston ran, he knocked
out the bunker with one grenade.
Now that's really somethin', huh?
Yeah.
(people grumbling)
(cop) We won't be long.
On your feet. Come on.
It's gonna be all over.
He's got a gun!
(shouting)
Take him down!
I'm not resisting arrest!
Stop hitting me, you sons of bitches!
I'm not the one! I'm not the one!
I'm not resisting arrest!
Police brutality!
This is police brutality!
I'm not resisting arrest!
(cop) Put him in the car!
(Oswald) Let me gm!
(cops, Oswald shouting)
(siren blaring)
(Martin Luther King)
We must, with positive action,
remove those conditions of poverty, ...
...insecurity and injustice...
...which are the fertile soil in which the seed
of Communism grows and develops.
These are revolutionary times.
All over the globe...
...men are revolting against old systems
of exploitation and oppression.
And out of the wombs of a frail world...
...new systems of justice
and equality are being born.
The shirtless
and barefoot people of the land...
...are rising up as never before.
"I can kill you whenever I please."
We in the West
must support these revolutions.
"But not today."
...because of comfort, complacency, ...
...a morbid fear of Communism
and our proneness to adjust to injustice...
...the Western nations that initiated...
...so much of the revolutionary spirit
of the modern world...
...driven many to feel that only Marxism
has the revolutionary spirit.
The ref ore, Communism is a judgement...
. . against our failure
to make democracy real...
...and follow through
on the revolutions that we initiated.
No, no. Why'd you have to do that?
To recapture the revolution...
Why didn't you know
this was coming, Edgar?
(coughs)
Last year the House was not smiling
on non eye-to-eye surveillance.
So I stopped.
We called Ramsey Clark to get a go-ahead
on tapping King's phone, but he refused.
Our "behind the fence" operations believes
that King's ally, Stokely Carmichael...
...is recruitin' a Negro army
to wage war on white America.
Wouldn't you, if you were them?
If this were only a civil rights issue...
...I'd vote for a King-Benjamin Spock
presidential ticket.
But, after last night, it's not.
You actually sound sad about it.
I respect King. He's an extraordinary man.
But now he's talking like a Maoist.
And if he convinces Negroes
not to fight in Vietnam, we'll lose.
And the first domino will have fallen.
We must step up our efforts
to discredit him.
Like your ridiculous suicide project?
"There is but one way out for you"?
That letter
attempting to drive King into despair...
...only alerted him
to the level of our surveillance.
We could create a film of him
with a woman other than his wife.
Using existing footage, we could insert him
in a film we make of a woman -
...a white woman.
The solution is more intense...
than just dirty tricks.
If you'll excuse us, the director
has a meeting at the White House.
Sit down!
You've enough plausible deniability
to last the rest of your nine lives.
A SIG force
can execute a wet-insert operation.
One day, he and his immediate circle
are just found dead.
Too many questions.
Americans believe the South
is still fighting the Civil War.
We find ourselves a cracker patsy, and
the motives become very black and white.
Another patsy.
Should we advise the president?
I work very hard to keep any president
from knowing I even exist.
Who will you order to do it?
I'll do it myself.
I have too much respect for the man.
(King) The nation is sick.
Trouble is in the land, confusion all around.
That's a strange statement.
But I know, somehow...
...that only when it is dark enough...
...can you see the stars.
And I see God working...
...in this period of the twentieth century...
...in away...
...that men, in some strange way,
are responding.
Something is happening in our world.
The masses of people are rising up.
And wherever they are assembled today...
...whether they are in
Johannesburg, South Africa;...
...Nairobi, Kenya; Accra, Ghana; ..
...New York City; Atlanta, Georgia;...
...Jackson, Mississippi
or Memphis, Tennessee...
...the cry is always the same:
"We want to be free!"
(people cheering)
(footsteps approaching)
Raul.
- I got the binoculars you sent me out for.
- Just put 'em down by your clothes.
I heard Dr King's stayin'
at the Lorraine Motel right behind here.
Our gun buyer's coming by
to look at the rifle.
Well, I gave it to you this mornin'.
Ihaveit
Look, uh, three's a crowd.
Here's a coupla hundred. Go to a movie
or something. Come back in a few hours.
Leave the Mustang. I'll need it later.
(King's voice)
Lord, I don't know what will happen now.
We've got some difficult days ahead.
But it really doesn't matter to me now.
Because I've been to the mountaintop.
(people cheering)
And I don't mind.
Like anybody, I would like to live a long life.
Longevity has its place.
But I'm not concerned about that now.
I just want to do God's will.
And he's allowed me
to go up to the mountain.
And I've looked over.
And I've seen...
...the promised land.
I may not get there with you.
But I want you to know tonight...
...that we, as a people,
will get to the promised land!
(cheering)
So I'm happy tonight.
I'm not worried about anything!
I'm not fearing any man!
Mine eyes have seen the glory
of the coming of the Lord!
(gunshot echoing)
(television)
...declarations of states of emergency
in several cities.
In Washington, DC...
(TV continues)
New York state senator Robert F Kennedy
has made an appeal for calm.
(Kennedy) I can also feel, in my own heart,
the same kind of feeling.
I had a member of my family killed.
But he was killed by a white man.
My favourite poet was Aeschylus.
And he once wrote...
..."Even in our sleep,
pain which cannot forget...
...falls drop by drop upon the heart...
...until in our own despair...
...against our own will comes wisdom...
...through the awful grace of God."
(voice on tape)
(siren blaring in distance)
All right, gentlemen.
Let's make this short
so we can all go home for Christmas.
Domestic unrest operations?
The Anita Hill thing
has lost steam since October.
Well, let it go. We played it right.
Unfounded allegations
will be flying around in no time. LA?
The Rodney King trial's been moved
to Simi Valley, as you instructed.
(beeping)
- Call back.
- Internationally, Bosnia-Herzegovina...
...is set for a February vote
on independence from Yugoslavia.
America couldn't care less.
I'm working on next month's
Oscar nominations.
- Any preference?
- I couldn't care less.
But I don't want the Bills
to win the Super Bowl.
As long as I'm alive, that doesn't happen.
Could be tough, sir.
Buffalo wants it bad.
So did the Soviets in '80.
You rigged the Olympic hockey game?
What's the matter?
Don't you believe in miracles?
The boss gave the Russian goaltender
a little pre-game good-luck pat on the back.
Unseen Novocain needle
on a bogus wedding ring.
Goalie's a little slow on the stick side.
Four-three, home team.
Payback's a bitch, Ivan.
- Well, gentlemen, if that'll be all...
- One thing internally, sir.
That "Spooky" kid who talked his way into
opening the X-Files, he feels like trouble.
He's mine to keep an eye on.
(beeping)
Gorbachev has just resigned.
There's no more enemies.
Merry Christmas.
If you don't have any plans, sir...
...we're all getting together
with our families out in Virginia.
You're more than welcome to...
Oh. Well.
Uh...
I have to, uh, see some, uh...
...some family.
(keyboard clicking)
(Andy Williams)
It's the most wonderful time of the year
With the kids jingle-belling
And everyone telling you "be of good cheer"
It's the most wonderful time of the year
It's the hap-happiest season of all
With those holiday greetings
and gay, happy feelings
When friends come to call
It's the hap-happiest season of all
(phone ringing)
Yeah?
(man) You'll never believe
what we just got for Christmas.
The craft matches the dimensions
of a vehicle spotted over Hanoi...
...when I was in Vietnam with the company,
that the Marines couldn't shoot down.
- Occupant?
- Critical.
Timing couldn't be worse.
The Roswell story we concocted
was gathering momentum.
Had them all looking in the wrong direction.
- With luck we'll get away with it.
- No luck tonight.
Our spy planes confirm
the Russians tracked entry
and have pinpointed touchdown.
Haven't you heard?
There are no Russians anymore.
Even if they're in the midst of ruin, the KGB
won't ignore an event of this magnitude.
Nor the Chinese, nor the Germans,
nor the British...
...or anyone with the capability
of discovering what happened here.
I'm certain each of them
has operatives advancing on us right now.
How many historic events have only
the two of us witnessed together?
How often did we make or change history?
And our names can never...
...grace any pages of record.
No monument will ever bear our image.
And yet, once again, tonight...
...the course of human history
will be set by two unknown men...
...standing in the shadows.
A living EBE could advance
Bill Mulder's project by decades.
Security Council Resolution 1013 states
any country capturing such an entity...
...is responsible
for its immediate extermination.
I'm the liar. You're the killer.
Your lies have killed more men in a day
than I have in a lifetime.
I've never killed anybody.
Maybe I'm not the liar.
I have a chance to go a lifetime
without killing anybody or any thing.
With all of our work
in the past 30 years, all of our victories,
if the world were to see this...
...it would destroy all we have gained
in a few hours.
Tonight, we have a new...
...enemy.
Heads.
Go ahead.
Make history.
(second gunshot)
(Frohike) At that point, your work
was getting attention from the top floor.
That's why you were brought in.
(man 1) Agent Scully, thank you
for coming on such short notice.
(man 2) Are you familiar
with Agent Fox Mulder?
Yes, I am.
- How so?
- By reputation.
Um, he's an Oxford-educated psychologist...
...who wrote a monograph on serial killers
that helped to catch Monty Propps in 1988.
Generally thought of as the best analyst
in the violent crimes section.
He had a nickname at the Academy.
Spooky Mulder.
Agent Mulder has developed
a consuming devotion...
...to a project outside
the Bureau mainstream.
Are you familiar with the X-Files?
(knocking)
Sorry. Nobody down here
but the FBI's most unwanted.
Agent Mulder. I'm Dana Scully.
I've been assigned to work with you.
Oh, isn't it nice
to be suddenly so highly regarded?
Who did you tick off
to get stuck with this detail?
I'm looking forward to working with you.
- I've heard a lot about you.
- Really?
I was under the impression
that you were sent to spy on me.
(Frohike) Henry David Thoreau wrote...
..."The mass of men
lead lives of quiet desperation."
His life has been anything but quiet.
Yet, I believe, nothing but desperate.
He's the most dangerous man alive.
Not because he believes in his actions...
...but because he believes these actions
are all which life allows him.
And yet, the only person
that can never escape him...
...is himself.
- (woman) Pivotal Publishing.
- Walden Roth, please.
- (woman) One moment.
- Walden Roth.
Oh, Mr Roth, hello.
Uh, this is Raul Bloodworth...
"author of Second Chance:
A Jack Colquitt Adventure.
Yes, of course, Mr Bloodworth.
What an active imagination!
Alien assassinations!
Is it too much?
I mean, is my imagination too active?
No, I love it.
As I've expressed in the letter...
...I wish to serialise your novel
in our publication, Roman A' Clef.
Many authors receive
their first printing in our publications.
(laughing) That's great.
Um, I had an idea about the artwork.
I thought it could have a kind of
Tom Clancy-ish kind of look...
Great! That's why we work
with young writers.
But you'll have to relinquish some control.
Of course. Of course.
After all, it is our publication.
And I can assure you,
we'll handle it with the utmost respect.
No, no, no. I'm sure you will.
I'm... I'm just excited.
Understandable.
Do you have an agent or attorney?
- No.
- That's fine.
It's a minimum agreement of $2500,
and you'll save yourself ten percent.
Well, that's fine, that's fine. Anything.
When do you plan to publish the story?
"Roman A' Clef" will be on the newsstands
the morning of November 12th.
(bell dings)
(man) Hey, buddy, you can't park there!
Excuse me, sir. Have you got
this week's issue of Roman A' Clef?
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
This isn't the ending that I wrote.
It's all wrong.
If you're gonna read it,
I gotta ask you to buy it.
Of course, I don't know why
anybody would wanna buy that sort of crap.
That be it?
Pack of Morleys.
Life is like a box of chocolates.
A cheap, thoughtless, perfunctory gift
that nobody ever asks for.
Unreturnable because all you get back
is another box of chocolates.
So you're stuck with this undefinable
whipped-mint crap...
...that you mindlessly wolf down
when there's nothing else left to eat.
Sure, once in a while
there's a peanut-butter cup...
...or an English toffee...
...but they're gone too fast
and the taste is fleeting.
So you end up with nothing but...
...broken bits filled with hardened jelly...
...and teeth-shattering nuts.
If you're desperate enough to eat those,
all you've got left is a...
...is an empty box
filled with useless brown-paper wrappers.
(Frohike) This is based
only on a story I read...
...in one of my weekly subscriptions
that rang a few bells.
I'll check on a private hacker source
who's been working on a few leads...
...that could produce definitive proof.
And then we'll have him nailed.
I can kill you whenever I please.
But not today.
Subtitles by Visiontext
(child) I made this.