Auntie Janet?
It's time, Auntie Janet. He's waiting.
We should hurry. We have papers to sign.
Just tell me when.
Don't you cry for me, dear.
I'm tired of the pain.
You're my angel of mercy.
Is she gone?
Something's wrong here.
(screaming)
(violin music)
(knock on door)
(speaks Russian)
(man) Vassily Peskow?
(man) Prisoner. Hey!
Pflsonen
I thought maybe you were dead.
How long have I been lying here?
Hours. I don't know.
The first time is bad. Very bad.
- They've done this to you?
- Yes.
It becomes easier each time,
until it kills you.
What did they do to me?
You have been exposed to the black cancer.
- What cancer?
- The cancer that lives in the rock.
Who are you?
I was a geologist.
Quite well known in my field, actually...
...but now I am just a test subject.
You helped them find the rock?
I was there when they brought up
the first fragments.
This was before the mining.
Before we knew what lived
in Tunguska rock.
How many men have died here?
Hundreds. Maybe more.
The search for a cure goes slowly.
Is that what they say the tests are for,
to find a cure?
No, no. They tell us nothing.
We are left to guess or imagine
the reasons for our torture.
But what else could it be?
What happened to the man
who was in the cell with me - Krycek?
He is most likely dining with the men
responsible for our torture.
I heard laughter when they left your cell.
- I'm not gonna die.
- No? Why not?
I have to live long enough
to kill that man Krycek.
- Where'd you get this?
- I made it... to kill myself.
It took me nearly two weeks.
By then I had lost the desire.
You'd rather suffer the torture?
It is wonderful, the persistence of life.
That rock we found buried
so deep in the earth...
...that anything could survive
down there against all reason...
No.
They will have to kill me themselves.
(Scully) We haven't been able to give him
anything but fluids for 48 hours.
(man) It doesn't help that
he's in a restricted environment.
Well, if he has been infected by some kind
of organism, we can't risk contamination.
Are you seeing anything?
The blood in the carotid artery
looks slightly thickened...
...possibly due to the decreased
heart rate and blood pressure.
Now what's this?
What the hell is this?
What is it?
I don't know. It looks like
it's concentrated around his pineal body.
- I think it's alive!
- (Scully) It looks like a nest.
Some kind of black vermiform organism
attached to the pineal gland.
- Apple?
- No. Thank you very much, though.
- (gasps)
- Oh, pardon me.
- Who are you?
- As a boy, my father had a farm...
...but not horses like these.
My name is Vassily Peskow.
Mr Peskow...
...I'm sorry, but you don't belong in here.
I am sorry, very sorry.
You are going to have to leave here.
I'm going to call you a cab.
But I have come here
to see you, Dr Charne-Sayre.
- Do I know you?
- No. I don't know how you could.
(horses neighing)
Agent Scully.
- Sir, what...?
- I've been trying to contact you for hours.
- The better part of a day!
- My cell phone was turned off.
You owe me some answers - answers I don't
have to the questions I'm being asked...
...about this missing diplomatic pouch.
The pouch presumably carried by the man
who was pushed off my balcony...
...and whose connection to
the known felon I harboured in my house...
...I'll have to explain to avoid perjuring
myself before a Senate subcommittee.
Which is a serious crime in itself,
is it not, Agent Scully?
Yes, sir. Sir, if I might explain.
The contents of that pouch - it contained
some kind of a biohazardous organism...
...that is in a contamination laboratory
at NASA Goddard...
...which is where I've been,
trying to determine its exact nature.
That pouch, do you know
what its intended destination was?
- No, sir, I don't.
- Well, I do, Agent Scully...
...because I bent some rules this morning
to find out who was to receive it.
- Who was it?
- Dr Bonita Charne-Sayre.
- Are you familiar with that name?
- Yes, sir. She's a well-known physician.
A virologist who's looked in on presidents.
She's also an authority on...
on variola viruses.
- Variola?
- Smallpox. She's been a vocal proponent...
...of eliminating the last remaining stores
of the smallpox virus...
...destroying the only remaining vials here
in Atlanta and in the former Soviet Union.
- Well, she was killed tonight.
- Killed?
A horse stepped on her throat
in a riding accident in Virginia.
(door unlocking)
(footsteps approaching)
(man speaking Russian)
- Where are we going?
- (speaks Russian)
Prisoner... is that your friend?
You have but one chance.
(speaks Russian)
(man yelling)
(yelling)
That's a nasty habit. It's bad for the health.
Health is the least of my concerns
at the moment.
Yes.
According to reports, your...
...personal physician suffered a serious
riding accident here on your property.
Dr Charm-Sayre was murdered.
BY Whom?
If I knew, do you think
I'd be standing here talking to you?
So...
You need me now.
A man of my capabilities, is that it?
This was a professional hit.
Really? And you out here
all alone and so vulnerable.
Were you sleeping with her?
Surely you wouldn't be so foolish
as to put the project at risk...
...for the sake of your personal pleasures.
Find her killer.
- Call off this Congressional investigation.
- I can't.
But Senator Sorenson
is an honourable man.
They are all honourable...
...these honourable men.
I heard Mulder was captured in Tunguska.
I hear now he's escaped.
Wake the Russian bear,
and it may find we've stolen its honey.
(horses neighing)
(men speaking Russian)
(groaning)
(running footsteps)
(speaking Russian)
No!
I'm sorry.
I, Dana Katherine Scully...
...swear to tell the truth, the whole truth...
...and nothing but the truth, so help me, God.
(gavel pounds)
I would like to read
from a prepared statement.
You may do so.
"I left behind a career in medicine
to become an FBI agent four years ago...
...because I believed in this country."
"I wanted to uphold its laws, to punish
the guilty and to protect the innocent."
"I still believe in this country."
"But I believe there are powerful men
in this government who do not."
"Men who have no respect for the law
and who flout it with impunity."
Ms Scully...
"I have come to the conclusion
that it is no longer possible..."
This is not a soapbox, Ms Scully. Your
statement will be entered into the record.
With respect, I would like to finish.
- This is not why we are here today.
- Then why are we here, sir?
Do you or do you not know
the whereabouts of Agent Mulder?
Are you or are you not aware
of Agent Mulder's present location?
I respectfully refuse
to answer that question, sir.
Agent Scully, you cannot refuse
to answer that question.
I believe answering that question
could endanger Agent Mulder's life.
You don't seem to understand.
Your response is not optional.
You are an agent of the FBI.
Then if I may please finish my statement.
"..That it is no longer possible for me
to carry out my duties as an FBI agent."
Are you tendering your resignation, Agent
Scully? Is that what you're trying to say?
No, sir.
What I am saying is that
there is a culture of lawlessness...
...that has prevented me from doing my job.
That the real target of this investigation...
...should be the men who are beyond
prosecution and punishment.
The men whose secret policies are behind
the crimes that you are investigating.
You have a legal obligation
to answer the questions posed to you.
Tell us what you know
about Agent Mulder's whereabouts...
...or you'll be held in contempt of Congress.
(buzzer)
(speaks Russian)
- No Russian.
- American?
Tell your husband I'm sorry about his truck.
The test?
Yeah.
- They kill everybody for the test.
- Why don't they kill you?
My husband makes deliveries.
They spare our lives.
But now, no truck. He is afraid.
- Well, I have to go now.
- No.
- They'll come looking for me, and for you.
- No!
- There are other ways.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
Grisha!
No arm... no test.
You don't understand. These tests,
this smallpox scar on your arm...
...it's some kind of identification.
You have to help me escape.
I'll help you escape.
You have to help me get to St Petersburg.
(heavy footsteps)
(door opens)
(man speaking Russian)
(screaming)
- You holding up?
- I've got plenty to read.
I can understand you
protecting Agent Mulder, but...
It is not just Agent Mulder
that I am protecting, sir.
Then what are you doing?
We were called before this committee
to answer questions about a murder...
...about an intercepted diplomatic pouch
that was to be delivered
to a prominent doctor...
...a woman who is now dead, as is the man
who was delivering the said pouch...
...the contents of which have infected
an exobiologist with a paralysing toxin.
Yet what are we stuck on here?
- The whereabouts of Agent Mulder.
- You mean it's the wrong question.
Several of the men
on this committee are lawyers.
It is my experience that
lawyers ask the wrong question...
...when they don't want the right answer.
Unless Agent Mulder has found
the answers they're looking for.
Or someone wants to make sure
he doesn't find them.
These are congressmen we're talking about.
I know that, sir,
and it is my natural inclination to believe...
...that they are acting
in the best interest of the truth...
...but I am not inclined
to follow my own judgement in this case.
So you're gonna follow Agent Mulder's.
Is that it?
His name is Vassily Peskow.
He was a KGB Line-X stringer
working out of Moscow Centre.
But how could this be?
How could the Russians know
we were working on our own inoculation?
- Six of us knew!
- Dr Charne-Sayre?
She was trusted. Absolutely.
Then I don't know.
Find this man! Find him!
If my intelligence sources are right...
...I think there's someone
who might save us the trouble.
- Mr Chairman, may I?
- Carry on.
Miss Scully, you've had a good long time...
...to think about the question
that was asked in our last session.
I want to give you the opportunity
to answer that question here today...
...so I can help our good chairman here...
...to get on with this proceeding.
I can't answer that question, sir.
I'm going to ask you again. Where is Special
Agent Mulder and why is he not here?
I'll answer your questions
about the man carrying the pouch.
- Agent Scully!
- About his murder...
...and my opinion about its connection
to the death of Dr Bonita Charne-Sayre.
Miss Scully, you'll get your chance...
- Or about the biotoxin within that pouch.
- Answer the question, Miss Scully!
(Mulder) What is the question?
(gavel pounding)
All right, let's come to order.
Agent Scully, do continue.
Yes, sir, if I may,
I would like to finish making my point.
What is your point, Miss Scully?
That the death of Dr Charne-Sayre,
given her field of expertise...
...suggests that she knew something
about the toxin, about its origins...
...and that knowledge may be linked...
...to the murder of the man in Assistant
Director Skinner's apartment building.
Miss Scully?
Yes, sir.
AD Skinner has informed me
that there has been an accident related...
An accident?
A doctor infected with the toxin has died
under suspicious circumstances...
...involving a theft of evidence...
...of the contents of the diplomatic pouch.
Well, we've gotten off
to a real fine start here.
I'm going to recess now
until this new matter can be explained...
...so we might then begin
moving in a forward direction.
Mulder...
I get to put my arms around you.
- Both of 'em.
- When did you get back?
- It's been a long, strange trip.
- Some other time.
There's been enough strangeness here.
I've made several connections
about what this toxin might be.
- So have I.
- Sir, I need your permission...
...to book two airfares
to Boca Raton, Florida.
It shouldn't take more than 12, 15 hours.
But if it does, I need you to stall the
committee tomorrow for the purpose of...
If you explain it to me, Agent Scully,
I'm gonna have to explain it to them.
I suggest you do everything in your power
to make it back for tomorrow's session...
...or I can't help you.
Boca Raton?
Dr Bonita Charne-Sayre
is a board member...
...and chief physician for a chain of elder-care
convalescent hospitals around the country.
Guess what one of her patients
died of in Boca Raton?
- Yes, what is it?
- Agents Mulder And Scully.
We need your permission
to speak with you or any of your patients.
- What about?
- May we come in?
Yes.
- When were these patients last checked?
- An hour ago, at bed check.
- This man's dead.
- What?
Scully!
These people are test subjects.
I think they've been poisoned.
Who gave these patients
their meds tonight?
I did.
OK, call 911. Tell them you've got
a quarantine of a biohazardous material.
Show us all of the entrances of the hospital.
We've got to seal this building immediately.
I don't understand
what you hope to learn here.
Everything that's happened, every death
we've seen can be traced back to one man.
But according to you, that man
is in Russia or possibly even dead.
Well, he isn't working alone.
Terry Edward Mayhew?
Can we talk with you?
Have a little off-the-record chat?
- About?
- Alex Krycek.
- Who?
- The man who set you up.
You and the members of your militia.
Name wasn't Krycek.
It was Arntzen or somethin' like that.
You met him in North Dakota,
salvaging material from a missile silo.
I never been in no missile silo.
I don't know nothin' about that.
This man Krycek,
or "Arntzen," as you call him,
how did he come into contact with you?
Off the record.
He came to us with some
building materials and some big ideas.
- What was he looking to build?
- Two...
...devices.
- Did he ever mention black cancer?
- Oh, yeah.
- What did he say?
- Developed by the Soviets.
Saddam used it in the Gulf.
You mean... used as biowarfare?
That's why they made
those servicemen take all them pills.
US government knew
about the black cancer.
They lied. Didn't have no cure,
no inoculation.
I think we'll quit right there.
I got nothin' more to say.
- Let's go, Mulder.
- You said there were... two devices.
What happened to the other bomb?
I ate it.
- Mulder!
- You wanna know about anarchy?
You don't tell me where that other bomb is,
I'll make sure you spend your prison time...
...putting a big smile on some convict's face.
Son of a bitch stole it, truck and all.
- Some storage garage.
- Where?
Terma, North Dakota.
Thank you.
Get the licence numbers for any two-ton
trucks stolen in North Dakota recently.
Have Canadian authorities
stop any vehicle fitting that description.
- Tell them they're looking for a bomb.
- What are you doing?
This has been a big setup
from the beginning.
Someone used Krycek, then Krycek used us.
Someone who didn't want
that rock in US hands.
But what's in Canada?
Where would you put this rock
if you didn't want it to be found?
Back in the ground.
Feflmsen
Fertiliser for my hothouse tomatoes.
Beautiful tomatoes all year, eh?
Thanks.
Go back to the refinery. See if you can
find anybody that knows about that truck.
(alarm beeping)
I would just as soon kill you,
but please don't make me.
My work is done.
(speaks Russian)
Mulder!
- (gavel pounds)
- I'd like to get started here.
- Miss Scully?
- Yes, I'm ready here, sir.
You have evidence to present.
This is what I've been told.
Yes, sir. Uh...
Evidence linking a number of deaths,
a great number...
...to a biotoxin that was
transported to US soil...
...by a courier who was also killed.
This was the man who was pushed
from the assistant director's apartment?
Yes. He has not been lD'd.
Do we have the name
of the individual who pushed him?
Yes, sir. Alex Krycek,
who is missing and possibly deceased.
And are you then in possession
of the pouch or its contents?
No, sir.
What evidence are you then
presenting us with today?
Documents and interviews...
...in support of a wide-ranging conspiracy
to control a lethal biotoxin...
...that is, in fact, extraterrestrial.
What, are we talking about
little green men here?
- No, sir. Not at all.
- Why is this so hard to believe?
When the accepted
discovery of life off this planet
is in every newspaper worldwide?
When even conservative scientists
are calling for the exploration
of Mars and Jupiter?
With every reason to believe that life is
thriving outside our own terrestrial sphere?
If you cannot get past this...
...then I suggest this whole committee
be held in contempt...
...for ignoring evidence
that cannot be refuted.
This is not why we are here today.
Then why are we here today?
I will suggest that we recess here until
the evidence can be properly evaluated.
Subtitles by Visiontext
(Child) I made this!