(screaming)
(gasping)
(screaming continues)
(baby crying)
(groaning)
(continues groaning)
- (child) All right, let's play some ball!
- Swing it in here.
- Strike!
- In what league?
Quit complaining. We already had to move
home plate cos you bitched about the mud.
(fielder) Nice pitch.
Come on, let him hear some chin music.
Throw a fastball!
Whoa.
- Nice hit.
- Go get it!
- Hey, come on!
- It went on the Peacocks' property.
Here's another one!
(pitcher) Come on, let's play!
Come on, baby, bring it home to Momma.
Come on, right here.
Come on, baby. Bring it home.
That's it. Ease up. Come on.
(fielder) Get to it.
Compression marks indicate the shovel
blade to be approximately 6% inches.
The deeper indentation on the right side of
the mark suggests a left-handed individual.
I've collected soil specimens...
...and, although numerous shoe impressions
remain from the game...
...I think dental-stone casts
will prove invaluable to the investigation.
And I've quit the FBI and become
a spokesperson for the Ab Roller.
Smell that. It's perfume. Eau de ball.
God, this brings back
a lot of memories of my sister.
All-day games out on the vineyard...
...ride your bikes to the beach,
eat bologna sandwiches...
Only place you had to be on time was dinner.
Never had to lock your doors.
No modems, no faxes, no cellphones.
If you had to do without a cellphone,
you'd lapse into catatonic schizophrenia.
You don't know me as well as you think.
My work demands that I live in a big city...
...but if I had to settle down, build a home,
it'd be a place like this.
It'd be like living in Mayberry.
Agents Mulder and Scully?
Hi. I'm Sheriff Andy Taylor.
For real?
Can't thank you or the Bureau enough for
00min' out. It's just me and my deputy and...
Hell, we never had anything of this nature.
Do you have any thoughts or suspects?
Population of Home is only a few hundred.
Everybody knows everybody, pretty much.
Any local women who were pregnant
and now suddenly aren't?
No. I just saw Mary Ellen and Nancy.
They're both doin' fine.
Hey, Sheriff, who lives in that house there?
Did you question them?
Cos they've been watchin' us.
That farm belongs to the Peacock family.
Three boys now - well, men.
Guess you could call them human.
Their folks were in a bad car wreck.
We suppose they died.
You suppose?
We tried to administer medical attention,
but the boys hauled the bodies away...
...took 'em home.
They haven't been seen in ten years,
so... we suppose they died.
Have you questioned the men?
The Peacocks built that farm
during the Civil War.
It still has no electricity,
no running water, no heat.
They grow their own food.
They raise their own pigs.
They breed their own cows.
Raise and breed their own stock,
if you get my meaning.
It is, however, the closest residence
to the crime scene.
Those boys are feeble, Agent Scully.
And sad. They wouldn't know
what you were talking about.
- They could have witnessed...
- Look, this town is my home.
I love it.
It's quiet. Peaceful.
I don't even wear a gun.
I've seen and heard some of the sick and
horrible things that go on outside my home.
At the same time,
I knew we couldn't stay hidden for ever.
That one day the modern world would find us
and my home town would change for ever.
And when I saw... it... in the ground...
...I knew that day had come.
Now I wanna find whoever did this.
But, in doing so, I'd like it if the way things
are around here didn't have to change.
I know this is iffy Bureau jurisdiction,
but I didn't know where else to turn.
So I called the Bureau in Pittsburgh,
and when I described the victim...
...they said I should see you.
We should take a look at the victim, then.
We don't have a lab or a morgue.
I've got a room down here,
might be a bit cleaner.
By the way, this is my deputy, Barney.
- Hie'?
- Fasten!
(phone rings)
I could use a bit more elbow room.
The thing is, see, folks have been
dropping in to ask about the case...
...and I wouldn't want anybody
to pop in and see this.
- You could just lock the door to the office.
- Folks know I never lock the door.
They'd start rumours.
Oh, my God.
Mulder, it looks as if this child...
...has been afflicted by every
rare birth defect known to science.
I'll have to order DNA typing
from the crime lab...
...but there appears to be abnormalities
associated with Neu-Laxova Syndrome...
...Meckel-Gruber Syndrome, exstrophy of the
cloaca... I don't even know where to begin.
I guess we can rule out murder
as the cause of death, huh?
I don't know about that.
There's evidence of occlusion
due to dirt in the nose and mouth...
...indicating the dirt has been inhaled.
There's something rotten in Mayberry.
Imagine all a woman's hopes and dreams
for her child, and then nature turns so cruel.
What must a mother go through?
Apparently not much in this case,
if she'd just throw it out with the trash.
I guess I was just projecting on myself.
Is there a history of genetic
abnormalities in your family?
No.
Just find a man
with a spotless genetic make-up...
...a high tolerance for being second-guessed,
and start pumpin' out the little tJber-Scullys.
- What about your family?
- Hm?
Aside from needing corrective lenses
and being abducted by extraterrestrials...
...involved in a governmental conspiracy,
the Mulder family passes genetic muster.
Scully, that child inside is a tragedy.
Some young parents, probably scared kids,
disposed of an unwanted birth.
In a very certain sense, infanticide is
involved, but this is not an FBI matter.
From what I know about genetic defects...
...that child isn't the result
of a single polygenic mating.
Let the local authorities investigate that.
Those defects
are autosomal-dominant disorders.
And from the degree, I'd say
mutations that go back many generations.
Scully, Sheriff Taylor implied
that the boys in that family...
...were not the type
that could easily get dates.
But he also implied
that they practise inbreeding.
Now, we all have a natural instinct
to propagate.
Do we?
There are theories
which pose that our bodies...
...are simply vehicles for genes
needing to replicate.
Yeah, but there's no sister,
the mother's been dead for ten years...
But if the instinct and need is strong enough,
they will answer it any way they can.
Now a woman gave birth to that child,
Mulder, and, my guess is, against her will.
And kidnapping is a Bureau matter.
Scully...
I never saw you as a mother before.
(fly buzzing)
No, there's no probable cause.
(Scully) They match.
- This room alone should convict 'em.
- If we can find them.
They probably bolted
when they saw us coming.
We'll alert Sheriff Taylor to get a warrant
for the brothers' arrest, put out an APB.
And check any prior
missing persons for a woman.
And check the vehicle identification
number on that Cadillac.
If the mother's alive,
they probably took her with them.
(raspy breathing)
I've issued descriptions and warrants
for George Raymond Peacock...
. . approximate age, 30, . ..
...Sherman Nathaniel Peacock,
approximate age, 26...
...and Edmund Creighton Peacock, 42.
- What about missing persons reports?
- Deputy Paster's on it right now.
Do you recall recently any vehicles
you found, thought to be abandoned...
...but which might belong to kidnap victims?
We saw a white Cadillac
in the Peacocks' front yard.
We get so many of those.
A car breaks down, they move on.
Well, we'll check on those in the morning.
You get some sleep, Sheriff.
You too, Miss Scully. Good night.
(dog barking)
Whoa! Don't move, don't move.
Damn.
- You still planning on making a home here?
- Nah. Not if I can't get the Knicks game.
Just as long as a brutal infanticide
doesn't weigh into your decision.
- Good night, Mulder.
- Good night, Mom.
Mulder, this lock is broken.
You don't have to
lock your doors around here.
(radio) Sometimes we walk
Hand in hand by the sea
And we breathe in the cool
Salty air
Andy, what are you doing?
Taking one good last look around...
before it all changes.
(sighs) Oh, honey, some to bed, huh'?
It will still be here in the morning.
Come on, honey.
You turn to me
With a kiss in your eyes
And my heart feels a thrill
Beyond compare
Then your lips cling to...
It's wonderful, wonderful
Oh, so wonderful, my...
The eldest dominant male in the pack moves
in to ensure that the prey has been killed.
Encircling the prey is a signal
to the others it is safe to...
(car radio)
(car approaches)
(engine idles)
What a moment to share
It's wonderful, wonderful
Oh, so wonderful, my love
Andy, what is it?
Hide, under the bed. I'm goin' for the gun.
But they wouldn't
have much meaning without you
Some quiet evenings
I sit by your side
And we're lost in a world of our own
You turn to me
With a kiss in your eyes
And my heart feels a thrill
Beyond compare
When your lips cling to mine
It's wonderful, wonderful
Oh, so wonderful, my love
(footsteps approaching)
(grunts and roars)
(grunting)
(grunts and sniffs)
- (Whimpers)
- (shouting)
(blows landing)
(radio) I feel the glow
Of your unspoken love
I'm aware
Of the treasure that I own
And I say to myself
It's wonderful, wonderful
Oh, so wonderful, my love
And I say to myself
It's wonderful, wonderful
Big American car.
I, uh... I came over to give him these reports
and, uh... and found them.
The, uh... the owner of the Cadillac was...
...was found and contacted in Baltimore.
She ran out of gas
and just left the car on the 119.
Other, uh... possible missing persons
are in the file.
And, uh... this came
from Federal Crime Lab overnight.
- Where are they?
- They're, uh... inside.
His chest is one big haematoma.
There's wood shavings embedded
in what's left of the cranium.
They really went caveman on 'em.
Damn it. The lab screwed up
the DNA test on the infant.
Multiple maldistribution, chromosomal
breakage, maldivision of the centromere.
You suspected these abnormalities.
Yeah, but this shows
far too many gene imbalances.
It would have to be a lab error.
This child's cells would've had
to divide triple-fold in cell metaphase.
Triple?
Hey, Scully, what if each of the Peacock
brothers was the father of that child?
Mulder, only one sperm in thousands
from a single individual...
...can penetrate an ovum membrane.
Let alone from three separate males.
What if generations of autosomal breeding
could produce such a mutation?
No. For that to be possible, there'd have
to be a weakening of the ovum...
...and that would be from a female member
of the Peacock family. And there aren't any.
Well, in any case,
they haven't ventured too far from home.
We should request backups
from Pittsburgh and pick 'em up.
That would take a whole day.
They may have a woman captive up there...
...who may have sustained
life-threatening injuries while giving birth.
Who knows what those men
have done to her. We should go there now.
We're outnumbered.
We could further endanger the victim.
I'll take you out there.
Then it's three against three. And this...
This should give us the advantage.
That was just a little bit
too Chuck Bronson for me, Scully.
Hang on a second, Mulder. Why...
Why would they kill Sheriff Taylor? He didn't
even question them about the buried child.
They probably heard about
the warrants for their arrest.
But how would they know?
He issued the warrants by phone.
Unless they heard us talking about it,
how would they know?
- We searched that house. They weren't home.
- Exactly. How could they know?
(Dig grunting)
I'm hungry-
(regurgitating)
All right. I'm ready.
You look fine.
They'll be comin' now.
We knew this day was gonna happen.
That they'd try to change the way things are.
All we can do about changin' things...
...is be ready for it.
Be ready for them.
Let 'em know this is our home...
...and this is the way it's gonna stay.
(Scully) Yup, they're up there.
I'll take the front. Their attention'll be taken by
the uniform. You can approach around back.
Are these vests absolutely necessary,
Deputy?
I've seen 'em fire muskets before.
I, for one, am not gettin' taken out
by some antique.
- This is Paster. I'm at the front of the house.
- We're getting into position.
I don't see anybody inside.
I'm going in.
Paster, no!
Paster's dead. The brothers moved in
like a pack of animals.
The eldest will move in
to ensure the prey is dead.
Encircling the prey is a signal
to the others that it's safe to approach.
What we're witnessing
is undiluted animal behaviour.
Mankind, absent in its own creation of
civilisation, technology and information...
...regressed to an almost prehistoric state...
...obeying only
the often savage laws of nature.
We're invading the den, trying to take
away their one chance at reproducing.
Which we're gonna do.
Even though we have the firearms,
I imagine the place is rigged with traps.
Yeah, but we can try
and divert them out of the house.
Scully, would you think less of me as a man
if I told you I was kind of excited right now?
There some secret farmer trick
to gettin' these things moving?
Naa-ram-ewe.
(bleating) Naa-ram-ewe.
Yeah, that'll work(!)
I baby-sat my nephew this weekend.
He watches Babe 15 times a day.
- And people call me spooky.
- (door opens)
Federal agents! ls anybody in here?
FBI! ls anybody in this house?
Is there anybody in here?
Oh, no.
(squeaking)
- No! Get out of here! Go away!
- It's all right, ma'am.
- We're federal agents. We're here to help you.
- Get out! Go away!
- Go away! Get away!
- Let's move the bed.
They've got her strapped
to some kind of board or something.
(woman continues screaming)
Take it easy, ma'am. It's all right. It's all over.
We're from the FBI. We're here to help.
We're gonna make sure that you're safe.
We're gonna make sure that you get home.
(crying continues)
Mulder, she already is home.
It's Mrs Peacock. She's their mother.
(hisses)
(yells)
(sobbing)
(Digs grunting)
- Where are you going?
- The others may have heard the screams.
What about her?
She's not going anywhere.
We may not be able to remove her, Mulder.
She doesn't appear to be held against
her will. I mean, I don't believe she is.
I'm sure she's an accessory.
We're only assuming.
We can't prove anything.
The way I think it goes here is that Edmund
is the brother and father of the other two.
So when Edmund was a kid, he could ground
the other two for playing with his things?
The brothers killed three people.
Tell her we're gonna bring them in.
And convince her that she's the one way
they can get out of this without getting hurt.
I'm gonna keep an eye on them.
Scully, watch your step.
This place is rigged.
Mrs Peacock?
Mrs Peacock, you are
in immediate need of medical attention.
Agent Mulder and I are here to help you.
This is our home. Why leave it?
- Whatever pain you may be in...
- I don't feel pain.
Runs in the family.
Have to check the boys,
see if they hurt themselves.
What about you? Even after the accident?
Right arm was torn off.
Saw it sittin' there
across my dead husband's lap.
Boys took me home...
...sewed me up, just like the family learnt
in the War of Northern Aggression.
Whole time, felt the same
as if been makin' breakfast.
They're such good boys.
Mrs Peacock, they murdered Sheriff Taylor
and his wife and Deputy Paster.
I can tell you don't have no children.
Maybe one day you'll learn...
...the pride...
.ihelove,“
...when you know your boy
will do anythin' for his mother.
Scully.
Federal agent! I'm armed!
Stop or I'll fire!
Mulder!
(gun empty)
(glass shatters)
I've got the mother!
(yelling)
(gunshot)
(brother groans)
Where's the other brother? Edmund?
Mulder, look.
Marks on the floor.
(Mulder) I looked everywhere. They're gone.
I've notified the state police and
the highway patrol. They've put out an APB...
...and are setting up a roadblock
over a 30-mile radius.
In time, we'll catch 'em.
I think time already caught them, Scully.
(music on car radio)
(Mrs Peacock) There, there.
Sherman and George were good boys.
We should be proud.
And you got to know, Edmund,
you can't keep a Peacock down.
There'll be more.
One day, there'll be more.
Now we have to move on...
...start a new family.
One we'll be proud of.
Find a new place to call ours.
A new home.
A brand-new home.
Wonderful...
Oh, so wonderful, my love
And I say to myself
It's wonderful, wonderful
Oh, so wonderful
My love
Subtitles by Visiontext
(Child) I made this!