GERRI KELLMAN: We had a tip off
some time ago,
New York Magazine working
on a substantial piece.
HUGO BAKER: They found a woman.
She was working the cruises
back in the mid 90s.
She says Uncle Mo asked for sex
with her and the other dancers
to get their contracts renewed.
So you know
when you had me destroy
those documents at Cruises?
Well, I kept a few.
(CHUCkLES) Where are they,
those papers?
- I'll never tell.
- (LAUGHS)
My dad has assured me that
this is not a major issue.
I don't want to overdramatize,
but Nan gets cold feet
and your dad could lose control.
Sometimes, I think you just need
a good old-fashioned
dinosaur cull.
- ROMAN: You barbecued him, live.
- Don't fuck with me!
It's over.
RHEA JERRELL:
Come on. Calm down.
You spoke to Logan
on the 13th.
I would like your resignation.
I don't appreciate
being hustled.
What the fuck?! Fuck off.
Get out of here. Fuck off!
You don't have a connection
for some powder, do you?
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Look out!
- KENDALL ROY: (CHUCKLING) No!
- Yes!
- No, no fucking way!
- No.
- What? Why not?
I mean, what, like,
what... what...
what are you even
gonna do with it?
I'm gonna look at it.
And make an assessment.
(KENDALL CHUCKLES)
No. How's Venice?
Kendall, this is not a request;
it's a demand.
I am not sending you a picture
of my dick. Okay? No.
No... Why?
NAOMI PIERCE:
I need it for my records.
I can't say this clearly
enough. Dick pic!
- I hear you.
- Dick pic!
(CHANTING)
Dick pic! Dick pic! Dick pic!
Okay, fine. Fine, fine,
fuck you, fine. Jesus.
- KENDALL: Fuck.
- (NAOMI LAUGHS)
I mean,
how do you even do this?
- So, like, what was wrong?
- Nothing. Nothing.
It was great. It was great.
Why didn't you send it to me
before?
Just because
after Dinosaur-gate, I just...
I wanted to get out
a clear statement
- and show them I'm not a sourpuss.
- Uh-huh. Yeah.
And y'know, I just,
I got into it.
And I wanted to show 'em
I have a positive plan, and...
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Oh, fuck.
No, Shiv.
Like, raw... raw is good.
It's memorable. Y'know, it's...
Find an audience with an income
and a pulse.
Yes, that's what I'm...
I'm not saying no to the center
because I'm... I'm saying
follow the ad revenue.
- No, yeah. No, sure.
- Can you hold this?
I think the cynicism
was pretty clear.
- What up, sis?
- Hey.
(TOM CHUCKLES)
Mega-dump and a line!
SIOBHAN "SHIV" ROY: This is
all... It's just... It's bullshit.
Because what it is,
really, it's just...
- it's displacement activity.
- Yeah.
I just need to find him
and ask him,
"Is it still happening?
Is it still me?"
Just, y'know, thrash it out.
You don't wanna thrash.
You wanna... Oh, hey there!
- Hi!
- How are you?
- SHIV: Hey, Peter.
- TOM WAMBSGANS: It's been...
It's been a long time.
Look, the shareholders want
a CEO successor named
before the shareholder meeting.
- They have made that clear.
- Mm-hmm.
So, if you're serious about us
as a dream ticket,
it'd be smart to be able
to preempt any bad stuff
that could come out if you
came under the spotlight.
Okay, okay.
Well, you want me to just
tell you
all the terrible things that I,
Roman Roy, have ever done?
How would you feel if I had
some oppo research done?
See what a tenacious
bottom-feeder
could grub up on you?
I'd say that sounds like fun.
Oh!
We went Blanch.
Oh, thank you, Gerri.
- ROMAN ROY: Thank you, Gerri.
- (WHISPERING) Blanch!
- For the internal investigation?
- Blanch and Partners.
Beautiful, soft-soaping fucks!
That interview
is going to be like
- slipping into a bubble bath.
- Yeah.
I'll just light a scented candle
in there, put some Eagles on
and start playing with myself.
(CHUCKLES)
They came. Look at them.
All the little piggies
at the trough. (CHUCKLES)
All the cruise noise,
a fucking nothing burger.
Reassured now
that they still love you?
LOGAN ROY: (LAUGHS)
Love. Fear. Whatever.
- (WHISPERS) Could I have a word?
- Yeah. Fine.
- Hey, Dad.
- In a minute, Shiv.
Uh, I... I'm sorry but I should
just... Y'know?
In a minute.
- MARCIA: Oh, hey.
- Hi.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
MARCIA: Hm?
♪ (FAIRGROUND MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
Hey, brother. I'll get one.
Sure thing!
That'll be 18,000 dollars.
NARRATOR: Ever feel like you're
being fed a bad investment?
Logan Roy and his family are
taking a once-great media brand
down a dead end.
Corporate Governance. Fail!
Acquisition strategy. Fail!
Succession planning. Fail!
The Roys are failing Waystar.
As a shareholder,
you can replace
Logan Roy's
rubber-stamp board right now.
Vote and let
this year's shareholder meeting
launch a fresh start
for Waystar,
the company you own.
Cool.
♪ (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS
ON VIDEO) ♪
FRANK VERNON: So Sandy and Stewy
have sent out thousands of them.
All major shareholders.
What does DF King say?
They say it might be time
to start getting worried.
LOGAN: Uh-huh.
Yeah, we've had
some disappointing feedback
on a couple of key investors.
LOGAN: Uh-huh.
The Pierce pursuit has played
badly in some quarters.
Jack, the Ulsterman is wavering.
He's four percent, isn't he?
We should have a conversation.
With that fat fuck?
Fuck that guy.
You should jam your dick in
his one good artery.
FRANK:
There's also one other person
who has a significant chunk
of stock
who we hear is no longer solid.
Your mother, Caroline.
- (LOGAN GROANS)
- KENDALL: Really? Mom?
What is she,
three percent voting stock?
GERRI KELLMAN: Uh-huh. We'd been
kinda counting on them.
I mean, we're at 36 percent.
Without their seven to add,
that is scary.
I'll talk to her.
Let her know this isn't funny,
and that she can kill you with
the wrong move.
Well, I imagine that's quite
a large part of the attraction.
We think that it'd be really
helpful to get you to the UK
for a personal appeal to Jack.
Like, tomorrow.
Roman, Kendall, Shiv
could hit their mom.
Okay. London. I'll take care
of the Ulsterman,
you're on your mom,
but keep it simple.
No Shiv.
I'm... I'm sorry... Wait. You mean
London, all of us, you mean?
- LOGAN: Mm.
- Are you sure we need to?
That's like, uh...
What are we? A fucking octopus?
Giving, like, reach-arounds to...
to every fish on the reef
now or...?
All right, relax,
branzino-porno-man.
LOGAN: It's fine. It's fine.
Colin will come.
Uh, Kerry, uh,
we can fix it, right?
You can reshuffle
the Dundee stuff?
KERRY:
About the journalism wing?
Yeah,
I'm sure they'll come to you.
Then straight to Singapore,
Christchurch, do it that way.
LOGAN: I need to make
some calls.
Kerry, we're hunkering. Frank,
Gerri, let's get down to it.
It's going to be an all-nighter.
- Hey, Rome.
- Yeah.
What's happening? Where's Dad?
- We're supposed to be talking.
- Ye...
Yeah, yeah, something came in.
He's hunkering.
He wanted me to tell you,
"Sorry, rain check.
Maybe in the a.m. Maybe."
Are your nips hard?
They must be, because
you are so out in the cold.
♪ ("SUCCESSION"
THEME MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
♪ (THEME MUSIC ENDS) ♪
- Uh, Tom Wambsgans.
- Yeah. Hi.
Thanks for making the time.
No, not at all. Big priority.
No, I managed to push all
my gropes to this afternoon.
- (LAUGHS) I'm just kidding.
- Yeah.
This is my colleague,
Stefan Strauss.
- Hey, hey, hi.
- How do you do?
- My name's Kenneth Chan...
- Hi.
...and we're with
Blanch and Partners.
Yes.
We are helping to investigate
historic sexual abuse...
- TOM: Uh-huh.
- ...and associated wrongdoings
at Brightstar Cruises.
- Sure.
- So, as head of the division
- we were hoping you could...
- Well, briefly, I, uh, I...
I followed Bill's long reign.
Um, I was but a minnow
trailing in the wake of...
of Bill,
the big sperm whale,
the legend. (CHUCKLES)
Sure, but in terms of your time
at Parks, were you aware
of any historical allegations
that had been dealt with
other than in a way outlined
in the corporate guidelines?
In my brief spell,
um, I don't...
at this time, recall anything
that at that time,
would have caused me
any real concern.
Okay. Well, we can take a dig
into that in a moment,
- but for now...
- Sure.
...in terms of records
and document-keeping...
Uh-huh.
Well, we need to locate all
written information
relevant to this investigation,
and safeguard it
from destruction,
negligence, malfeasance.
Are you aware
of any document destruction
which might hinder
our inquiries?
I... I think, um...
You know what? I...
You know what? I just...
I've just realized
we're gonna be here for a while,
and I wanna give you
my best attention,
but I really need to pee.
(CHUCKLING)
W... We'd rather you stayed here.
I've got this
pathetically weak bladder.
I'm like an old woman
who's had a baby somehow.
- So, I'm gonna...
- KENNETH: Well...
But I'm... I'm so sorry.
- I'll be right back. Okay.
- (LAWYERS MUMBLE)
Who's the pilot today?
Not Serge, right?
- No, sir. Serge is off rotation.
- LOGAN: Good.
I like a boring bastard
flying me.
Serge always looks as if
his dick's still wet,
and he's gonna give me the name
of a good fucking pinot.
Are you all right, son?
Mm. Mm-hmm. Yeah, I'm good.
Thanks for the ride.
LOGAN: It's good to see you.
Good to see you, too, Dad.
I hope we can swing it with Mom.
Yeah, I... I was gonna say,
you know,
that thing up at Argestes...
Oh. No, yeah.
Mm-mm. It's not...
I... I didn't even know
you were there.
I mean, if I did, I would...
Y'know?
Oh, I know. Yeah, I know. Sure.
Did I even make contact?
Um... I don't... think s...
Yeah, I'm not quite sure
what we're talking about,
- to be honest.
- Because...
that's not something I'd do.
Y'know?
Yeah, I know. I know that.
I know. I know.
Fucking...
cars, buildings, everywhere.
RHEA JARRELL:
He didn't tell you I was coming?
No. No, he did not.
For a media guy, he's not
the greatest communicator.
RHEA: Thank you.
I was going anyway to check out
some theater, and he asked
would I talk through
a couple things with him.
- Bounce some stuff.
- KENDALL: Uh-huh.
- You feelin' bouncy?
- Honestly?
A little deflated.
After all the retreats
I've done,
you know,
still got a bit of an ego.
Uh-huh.
Hey! Hi! (CHUCKLING)
(CHUCKLING) Hey!
Oh. Hey, Rhea.
- Dad, Rhea's here.
- LOGAN: Yeah, well...
Not a big deal.
ROMAN: Course it's not
a big deal. Why would it be?
- LOGAN: It's convenient.
- Okay, well, here we go.
Roy boys on tour,
and we got 'em in all sizes.
Alpha, beta, cuck.
He's fucking leaving
the country?
Rather than speak to me.
How long have you known this?
Plans change, so...
He wanted to apologize.
Bullshit.
- TOM: Hey.
- You...
Hey, Shiv. Hey.
- Hey.
- What... Hey, oh...
- Do you know he's gone?
- TOM: Can I ask you about something?
Can you believe you this?
He's gone.
And his fucking flunkies
didn't even tell me,
running interference for him.
I won't have it.
I'm not gonna chase him
around the party
like a schoolgirl
with a crush.
No, absolutely.
Hey, um, I just wanted to check
it definitely is bullshit
this...
this internal investigation?
Y'know, he hasn't even responded
to the memo.
TOM: Because that didn't feel
all that bullshitty.
It wasn't all softballs?
You ever been hit in the face
with a softball?
I mean, just how inside this
are you?
'Cause there isn't a world,
is there, in which I get
hung out to dry, in which
I have to play the fuckbag?
- Is there? I mean...
- No.
...he supports me, right?
Logan?
I mean, never mind the jokes
and the "ha ha,"
he's not gonna fry me, is he?
No, Tom. No. I... You know what?
I think I have to go out there.
I have to... go and fix this,
okay?
You okay?
Sure.
RHEA: Oh, sure. "Sure."
Don't poke the bear.
He can take anything.
Load him up.
Oh, I don't fucking know.
All this energy.
I'm gonna have to fight now
for every fucking
shareholder vote.
My ex-wife,
my old friends turning.
I kill Sandy. Sandy kills me.
So fucking what?
The next Zucker-fucker
comes along
and swallows you whole.
Shits you out as an app.
(WEAKLY) Yeah...
We've had some private polling
on potential next CEOs,
who'd play well.
I'd value your thoughts.
On the kids?
Who's got it? Huh?
I... (CHUCKLES)
I could do with a clear eye.
As execs, okay. Well...
Shiv thinks she's smarter
than she is.
Roman could actually be good,
but, um...
but nowhere near right now.
Kendall's... I don't know.
It's like you put him
in a big diaper,
and now he can shit himself
whenever he likes.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Uh, he has all the shots
but he doesn't know
when to play them.
- (LOGAN LAUGHS)
- I... I don't know. (CHUCKLING)
Yikes.
Look at them.
Fucking coochie-fucking-coo.
Yeah, I haven't seen him
like this for a while.
Yeah, not since Sally Anne
and the summer of the horses.
- Remember that shit?
- Right.
- ROMAN: Well...
- Do you think, um...
like, do you think
they're fucking?
Oh my God, could you imagine?
Like a rhino fucking
a hummingbird.
She'd have to go cowgirl, right?
Otherwise, he'd just like
snap her like a candy cane.
Dude, are you... like...
talking yourself hard right now?
Boys! Come on through.
ROMAN: Come through, I guess.
All right. Come through what?
- So...
- ROMAN: Mm-hm?
Shiv's memo.
KENDALL: Okay, we're...
we're... we're what?
We're putting the concept
of Siobhan on the table
for general discussion?
You're tearing apart
my sister's pious bullshit
for your entertainment?
I had a dream like this once.
It's just good
to air some views.
ROMAN: Mm.
KENDALL: Okay.
Yeah, I mean, I think
the... the twin quotes
from Thomas Aquinas
and Amelia Earhart really...
- (ALL LAUGH)
- ...kick us off with a bang.
ROMAN: Wow, so many pictures.
All the smiling children,
all the various hues, that...
that melted the heart
- of even this hardened racist.
- (RHEA LAUGHS)
I... I like the spacing.
Um... Luxurious.
It is. But the protein.
Well, there's no shortage
of concepts, for sure.
It's a rich gumbo of ideas
and buzz words.
Look, we should be gentle.
It's easy to be overly critical
of the workings
of a major corporation
when you have no experience
running one.
I... You can't blame her
for a lack of experience.
Well, sure you can. Just watch,
you'll get the hang of it
- soon enough.
- (RHEA LAUGHS)
GREG HIRSCH: No, thanks.
But those are really good.
Those are organic. I'll grab him
and see what's...
Hey, Tom.
- TOM: Hey, Greg! How ya doin'?
- Good, good. Yeah.
- Hey, bud.
- Good, yeah. Just busy.
Just, uh... Why are you, um...
- Sure, what's going on?
- Um, I'm just have a few, uh,
- a few pals over for dinner.
- Ooh, look at you, Fancy Dan.
The Greg Man. (LAUGHS)
What are you talking about?
- Hey.
- Welcome to the next wave.
Just a talking shop for renewal.
(MOCKING) "Just a talking shop
for renewal."
- (TOM LAUGHS)
- (CHUCKLES FEEBLY)
No, no, no. It's good.
It's good. We're good.
Listen, I wanted to, um,
I wanted to ask you.
I was in the area, actually,
that's why I came round.
I wanted to ask you,
uh, how was today with the guys?
The interview?
Oh, yeah. Um...
Uh, yeah. Okay, I...
- Uh, a little bit jittery.
- Mm-hmm.
Uh, a bit of a stress comedown.
- Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
- You know, I, uh, got a haircut.
Even though I didn't really need
a haircut.
- Right.
- I think I just wanted someone
to touch my head, you know.
Soothing.
- And, um, I guess I found it a little bit stressful...
- Uh-huh. Great. Great.
So, here's my thing.
Greg, you know the papers?
The copies? I want them.
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah.
I did my part of the deal.
You got the office,
a pretty little Gustav Klimt
poster up there,
and now it's time for me
to habeas the corpus.
GREG: No, right, right. I... I...
I mean, I just guess, uh...
I... I just guess that they're,
like, my insurance policy.
Yeah, but you don't need
an insurance policy.
Well, in case things
were to turn nasty.
They're not gonna turn nasty.
Okay? No one's gonna
break your legs, y'know?
Okay, well that feels
a bit nasty.
But it's the insurance
which is causing the nastiness.
If you were uninsured, you'd be
a lot safer. Ironically.
Okay, well,
they're not actually here,
- so I don't really know what to tell you.
- Okay. Greg. Greg, Greg. Look.
Okay, you played your hand
very well. I like it.
- (CHUCKLES)
- I do.
But we need to end this now.
Or I tell Logan that you took
copies of sensitive documents.
O... Okay, that...
Well, I don't...
Okay, well, I...
I keep them at...
I keep them at the office.
You keep them at the office?
Yeah. 'Cause they're work.
I'll go... I'll go in early,
and I'll give them to you
first thing tomorrow.
Right. Right. (SNAPS FINGERS)
But... But... But...
Except I can't trust you.
- (SIGHS)
- Okay, it's not personal.
I just can't trust you.
So, in a friendly way,
I'm staying here tonight,
and I'm gonna travel in
with you tomorrow,
and I'm gonna go with you
to wherever you have the papers,
- and then later, together...
- Dude.
...we're gonna dispose of them
off-premises.
And if you squeal
or you try to take copies,
- I'll break your legs.
- (CHUCKLES)
Sorry, I hope you didn't mind
eating in. But it's just...
paps in this town,
fucking animals.
Oh, sure. If only someone
had some influence over them.
(CHUCKLES)
RHEA: You okay?
Ah.
Siobhan's coming over.
Apparently, she's all fired up.
I imagine you've seen
a few temper tantrums
- from your children.
- LOGAN: Oh, I don't know.
She wants answers.
Okay.
What if you're right?
What if she doesn't have it
in her?
That's not exactly what I said.
I worry for her.
Y'know, maybe I jumped too fast.
Nothing's been said publicly
though, right?
With Kendall,
it wasn't the best situation.
Maybe I should just say
"Fuck it" and let her do it.
I don't fucking know.
When does she get in?
LOGAN: Tomorrow.
You know,
if you wanted me to...
I think I might be able
to help you make this go away.
It's delicate.
RHEA: Would you like me to try?
Let me see what I can do.
(SWALLOWS)
You wanna stay over or what?
Oh. Okay. Um...
I wasn't expecting that.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
GERRI: Okay, so look.
From the oppo research on you,
- I'm gonna ask you some yes-nos.
- ROMAN: Uh-huh.
GERRI: Did you get jerked off
by your personal trainer
at the end of sessions?
Um... Nope. No. No, I did not.
- Libel.
- GERRI: Uh-huh.
There's rumors
of a face tattoo situation.
Uh... no memory of that. No.
- Uh-huh.
- KENDALL: Hey, dude.
Have you seen this?
From UK Comms?
Oh, what?
- Oh. Hey, Gerri, have you...
- GERRI: What?
...seen this?
I'll call you back.
- Where's Dad?
- Shit.
- Is he awake?
- I don't know.
Is he, uh... like, on his own?
Did Rhea go home?
They were having Scotches
when I came in.
I was at Edward's hell hole
in Mayfair. When did you get in?
Did you bring a piece of ass
back with you?
- 'Cause I think I heard.
- He needs to see this.
You think... Should I wake him?
I think so, yeah.
Fuck it, he needs to see this.
I'm gonna get him up.
ROMAN:
Wake him up. Definitely.
(SING-SONG)
You're gonna see him boning.
Dad.
ROMAN: Just go in.
He needs to see the story.
- Go in.
- (WHISPERS) Dude, fuck you.
Okay, I'm coming in, Dad.
- Dad.
- LOGAN: Huh?
Where the fuck am I?
GERRI: The family's line
is emotional distress.
KAROLINA NOVOTNEY: Yes,
they're saying you punched him,
which caused him, in effect,
to drive his car into the river.
LOGAN:
I did not punch anyone.
Yeah, this is, um...
this is incorrect.
LOGAN: I never touched that kid.
Well, I mean...
shouted a little.
- Jostled a glass but...
- Stop mumbling!
At... At most, you shouted.
Oh! Did... Oh, I shouted him
into the river?
No, that's what I mean. I'm...
I'm saying that
it's not right. This...
(SIGHS)
I should never have come.
I walked into a trap.
I've been badly advised.
You hear that, Gerri? Karolina?
- Yeah.
- Yes, we heard.
- LOGAN: Is Hugo there?
- Uh-huh.
I don't think we have
any huge concerns
in terms of legal liabilities,
right?
Oh, fuck no. No, they're saying
you owed a duty of care
and threatening legal action,
but that won't fly.
HUGO BAKER: The issue is we hear
that they may come to the US,
and appear on the Morning Juice
with this,
- which would not be...
- GERRI: From what I hear,
what they really want
is actually just the apology.
Uh-huh.
- GERRI: A personal apology.
- No.
HUGO: Sure.
I guess the only thing is,
in terms of the proxy battle...
GERRI: It's Sandy's tabloid
that's stirring this up.
- They went and interviewed them.
- Of course.
GERRI: It's a transparent effort
- to rattle our shareholders.
- Uh-huh.
HUGO: How about we offer
a visit to the family?
We may be able to get
a statement out of them
absolving you of guilt.
Just say sorry,
and for all the distress.
But we make it clear
that Sandy and Stewy
are beating their drum
with the bones of a dead kid.
So it rebounds.
You think that gets me out?
- KAROLINA AND HUGO: Definitely.
- GERRI: Yes.
LOGAN: Yeah.
Well, I suppose everybody
has to apologize
for everything nowadays.
Okay. Okay. Set it up.
- HUGO: Great.
- GERRI: Will do.
On it.
Bye, guys.
You have a fun night, Dad?
- What the fuck does that mean?
- ROMAN: Nothin'.
- Oh, hi.
- Hey.
- Okay. All right.
- NAOMI: Hey.
KENDALL: Uh, Dad.
You remember Naomi Pierce.
Uh, she was in Venice
at the Biennale,
so, it was easy for her
to pop over and...
ROMAN:
Ah, Italian take out. Nice.
Thanks for having me.
How's your cousin?
She actually is taking
the month off
- to visit British Columbia.
- LOGAN: Oh, I bet she is.
NAOMI: I think
the whole sale experience
- was quite draining for her.
- Yeah.
Ooh, I can only imagine.
Naomi, uh, send her my love
and the whole fucking gang,
won't you?
Boys, I need five on strategy
- in private.
- KENDALL: Yep.
- NAOMI: Mm-hmm.
- I'll, uh...
- Later.
- I'll see you over there.
Bye.
Nice.
(DOOR SLAMS)
So... on your mom.
- Probably just bullshit.
- Mm-hmm.
She's always been
a piece of work.
See if you can sweet talk her.
And if necessary,
make her an offer
that brings her back into line.
I need her three percent.
Well, what do we have
to play with?
LOGAN: Well, cash is difficult
because it looks like a bribe,
- but, uh...
- So...
reopen the divorce settlement,
maybe?
Yeah.
Offer her ten million.
See if she pipes down.
I'll go as high as 50,
but I won't be happy.
Exciting. Grinding Mom down.
So... looking forward to dinner?
- (SCOFFS)
- Yeah, last time I ate there,
it was three muddy trout for six
and fill up on mustard.
(GIGGLES) Oh, poor bastards.
Slim pickings, huh?
Whatever happens,
we need her vote.
- Whatever it takes.
- Whatever it takes. Right.
All right, Dad. Got it.
But I don't like being fucked.
So, screw her out a bit.
Anything you save under the 50,
we can split.
Well, that oughta cover
the... subsequent therapy.
- Yeah. No, no. I'm kiddin'.
- Yep. Me, too.
- We need her.
- Got it.
(DOOR CLOSES)
What, did Rhea stay late or...
Did you guys...
Why?
Uh, nothing.
No. No, no, no.
I mean, just, um...
I... I just wanted to say...
and don't take this
the wrong way,
like...
Are you sure this thing
with Rhea is a good idea?
It... It feels like...
Yeah, it feels like she could be
playing you?
- I can take care of myself.
- KENDALL: Sure.
I... I know you can take care
of yourself,
and you know, your business
is your business. I'm just...
You're the one
who's cunt-struck.
Whoa. Okay, uh... (SCOFFS)
No, I... I'm... I'm just...
It's just maybe not a good look.
The old f... Not...
Not the old fool, but, y'know...
- That... That's not what I'm saying.
- LOGAN: Uh-huh.
I'm... I'm saying that's how
she could make you seem.
Just... Just being honest.
- I appreciate it.
- (KENDALL SIGHS)
Okay, well, uh...
I think Na... Naomi
wants me to take her
to The Regent's Park Zoo.
Apparently, we're in a fucking
Simon and Garfunkel song.
- So, um, I'll travel to Mom's...
- I think we should do
a bit of, uh, brainstorming.
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah.
LOGAN: Will you come with me?
As in...
Down to the boy's family.
Right.
I mean...
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Oh. Okay.
We should stick together
on this.
Don't you agree?
♪ (MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
Is Dad here?
ATTENDANT: Would you like
a drink of some kind?
Uh, no, I'm fine. Thanks.
♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
Hey, what's poppin', Malala Roy?
Uh, where's Dad?
ROMAN:
Oh, were you chasing the dragon?
He is ghost. Again.
- Isn't that cool?
- For fuck's sake. Where is he?
He's seeing the Ulsterman, no?
ROMAN: Paying homage
to a dead kid's parents.
He's seeing the Ulsterman
at the races.
Hey, really very much enjoyed
your little me-mo.
- What the fuck?
- (GIGGLING)
Oh yeah, it was, uh...
very compelling.
It was like eye crack.
W... Uh, well, has Dad read it?
ROMAN:
Has he not got back to you?
'Cause he read it yesterday,
so he has had a ton of time.
- For fuck's sake.
- (GIGGLING)
Yeah, we all read it. It was
a little round table thing;
me, Ken, Dad, Rhea.
Rhea? Rhea's in town?
Do you know nothing
of the company
you're supposed
to be taking over?
Y'know, Waystar?
Waystar Royco?
We do hate speech
and roller coasters.
- (PHONE RINGS)
- Fuck you.
TOM: Okay.
Okay.
Um, before I hand these over,
could... could I actually make
one final request?
Uh, Leo, my neighbor here,
uh, he sneezes
like a cartoon character,
so, I was thinking maybe
a corner office...
Don't overplay your hand,
Gregory.
Come on.
- Okay, w...
- Come on.
"Secret," Greg?
Yeah?
But not "Top Secret."
Interesting.
Just "Secret," that's smart.
Just so people know, you know,
- that these are secret.
- They're secret. Yeah.
I don't know, 'cause sometimes,
the janitors,
they come and throw stuff out
and, uh...
But look, the actual envelope
says "Receipts."
Ooh! But they're not, in fact,
receipts.
(GASPS) Greg!
You're a criminal mastermind.
What polyglot genius
could ever hope
to crack your impenetrable code?
- Shut up.
- God.
- Easy.
- Sorry.
RHEA: Thanks for making time.
Yeah, well, uh, you know,
an unexpected, uh, gap
in the schedule.
And you what,
you just happen to be here?
- Seeing some theater.
- Oh, lovely.
"See some theater."
And your dad offered me
the ride.
And look, it's...
it's good to chat.
Because he's...
he's a very...
Your dad's a tough guy. I...
I took it pretty hard
getting fired.
Yeah, sure. Sure, and...
you know, we appreciate
what you tried to do for us.
But he's been kind.
He's been kind to me.
People don't talk
about his kindness.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah, no they don't.
Not a great deal.
Look, I'm being very frank.
I hope that's okay.
- Is it too much or bad?
- SHIV: Yeah... No, uh...
Thank you.
I feel we have a connection
and I like you.
And I know what it's like
to fight your way through
in our industry, you know?
Yeah. No, sure, I...
I appreciate it.
Because you must be fond
of Marcia.
So...
Uh... yeah,
we have a, um, relationship.
Yeah, you know, a very...
functioning relationship.
(CHUCKLES) Well, look,
yeah, I don't know what to say.
I just like you
and I... I...
Your father's
a very appealing man,
- and I hope...
- No, it's fine.
It's... No, it's good to check
before you fuck someone's dad.
- (BOTH LAUGH)
- SHIV: I mean, yeah.
Do your due diligence,
your paperwork.
Do I need to sign like
a release form or...?
I feel like a total idiot,
- so, congratulations.
- (SHIV LAUGHS)
- No, you shouldn't. It's... No.
- RHEA: No?
'Cause you play your cards
pretty close.
Oh, who says I have cards?
But you're okay?
Uh... honestly, no.
I feel like a flame-roasted,
wood-fired dipshit.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah, I did the thing that
I said I was never gonna do,
and...
Now, I don't know.
I don't... I don't know.
Uh-huh. Well, the problem is
it just so happens
you're very smart
and talented, Siobhan.
Thank you.
But... (SCOFFS)
what does my dad think?
Right?
I've managed to get myself
into this situation
where "What does my dad think?"
is my entire fucking universe.
Well, I mean... maybe...
Maybe, isn't now the time
to just let him know, you know?
You have options.
(SCOFFS) Okay, yeah,
but I can't bluff him.
Sure, but... I happen to know
there's a media operation
in need of a dynamic new CEO.
And I happen to know Nan Pierce
has a certain regard for you.
And I happen to know
she wouldn't mind
putting a fucking sharp,
burnt stick
in your dad's cyclops eye.
(CHUCKLES) Oh...
Uh, me at Pierce?
That's never gonna happen,
is it?
RHEA: Uh, I don't know.
But I can get it floated
with clean hands,
and they'll consider it
for sure.
Then it's all upside.
Keep it in your back pocket,
lay it out to your dad,
or even take the job.
Well, uh...
let me think about it.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
And, uh...
So, what are...
whatcha doin' tonight, Dad?
Tonight? Cheltenham.
- Uh, the Ulsterman.
- Oh, yeah.
Watch him eat a fucking horse.
Then, I don't know.
I... You know,
I might have dinner with Rhea.
Yeah. Great.
Yeah, she's never been
to Cheltenham.
Yeah, well, it could be nice
to see Cheltenham.
Excuse me?
You got a problem?
No.
♪ (MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
Look at this place.
- MAX: How you doin'?
- COLIN: Hi. I'm Colin.
- Max. Pleasure.
- He's with you?
- Yeah, he's the one.
- Yeah.
So, what do we got? Mom? Dad?
MAX: And the boy's uncle
is here also.
Ah. (SIGHS)
This is Phillip Cleave.
He'll take a few photographs.
- I'll put together some press comments.
- Uh-huh.
LOGAN: Uh...
Actually, Ken.
Why don't you come in with me?
KENDALL: You want me...
Well, you know,
it looks a little weird.
You know,
I bring you all this way,
and you sit in the car
like a Labrador. Come in.
MAX: Paul, Andrew's uncle.
Paul, pleased to meet you.
Logan Roy.
And this is my son, Kendall.
Oh, uh... Hi. Hello.
PAUL: Steven and Theresa
are in the lounge
- if you'd like to come in.
- Please.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
LOGAN: Ah, Theresa. Steven.
STEVEN: Hi. Hello.
- Steven.
- Logan Roy.
THERESA: (DISTANT)
Would like a tea or a coffee?
LOGAN: Well, uh, yeah,
that's kind.
I'm good. Thank you.
Thank you so much for seeing me.
You know, this has been
a terrible tragedy.
STEVEN: Of course.
THERESA: Oh, sorry. Take a seat.
(MUFFLED CONVERSATION CONTINUES)
(DOOR OPENS)
PAUL: I'm doing teas.
Oh, um, no, not for me.
Thank you. Thanks.
PAUL: Water?
Uh, yes. Actually, thank you.
Yes, please.
PAUL: You staying
at your mother's?
Um, yep. Yes, I am.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Okay, let's go.
KENDALL: Hey, Dad.
Do you think I should maybe
say something to them?
No.
♪ (MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
Poor bastards.
They've been through the ringer,
you know?
Fuck knows how they cope.
They're embarrassed, really.
They knew he was a druggie.
Yeah, that is life.
Don't forget it. Right?
(SIGHS)
You know, there's nothing
to be ashamed of. Our stuff.
We give them a bit of a laugh,
some decent TV to watch,
news that doesn't talk down
to them.
Good fucking people.
Nice fucking folk.
(LOGAN SIGHS)
You know, Dad won't be pleased.
Well, she demanded
my attendance, so...
Oh, more scared of Mom
than Dad, huh? Interesting.
What is this?
A museum of wartime food?
This is for display, right?
None of this edible.
SHIV: (SIGHS) What did we buy
last time we came?
Um...
It was a Scotch egg that
I thought was a huge arancini,
and some lard.
I'm just gonna get a banana.
Can't get food poisoning
from bananas.
You'd be surprised.
GREG: Hello?
Hey, hi... hi... hi, I'm involved
in a criminal conspiracy.
"Oh, really?"
Yes, yes, I am.
Yes, I... I destroyed some papers
that I shouldn't have.
"Oh, did you?"
Yes, I did. Is that bad?
"Uh, yeah, that's bad.
Yeah, that could be bad.
You could go to jail.
Yeah, would you like that?
Would you like that,
pretty boy like you?
Would you like it?
Oh, you might...
Oh, you might even like that."
Male rape.
Rape of the male.
(SIGHS)
That was lower jacket pocket.
Lower jacket pocket.
(CLEARS THROAT)
This is inside pocket.
All aboard inside pocket.
Here I am, I'm moving.
I'm moving. I'm moving.
Brisk movement.
This is faster.
Okay, wind is blowing.
And I'm talking louder.
"No, I don't remember, Greg.
No, I don't remember." Okay.
(PHONE PLAYS BACK CONVERSATION)
...criminal conspiracy.
"Oh, oh, really?"
ROMAN: Thank you, sir.
SHIV: Mom?
CAROLINE COLLINGWOOD: Hello!
- Hey!
- CAROLINE: Hello!
- Hi. Hello.
- Siobhan.
Ro-Ro!
Hey, Mommy!
Thank you for coming down.
Yeah, well,
just following orders.
Like a Nazi.
Mm-hmm. Exactly. Right?
Well, you're in the country,
so what were you going to do?
Go out whoring in Soho?
Yeah, that would have been
the first choice.
Well, look, Kendall's
gone to the pub apparently,
so, I've just had a little bit
of pigeon done.
Didn't think anyone would be
feeling terribly hungry.
I know I'm not.
SHIV: No, right.
- Don't want a great...
- Course not.
...bolus of gubbins.
- Take a plate.
- Thank you.
Catch.
So, how are you?
Well, I might just as well
ask you
if you're going to go
into all that.
Uh...
It was... (CHUCKLES)
Wasn't intended
as an aggressive question, Mom.
It's...
CAROLINE: No, I'm fine.
Rory's wonderful.
Mm-hmm.
CAROLINE:
So, should I be mother?
Yeah,
why don't you give it a go?
(MOCKING LAUGH)
Yes, well, I'm sorry it's
not a 48-ounce T-bone steak
with truffle fries,
but there we go.
Some of us don't want
coronary heart attacks.
It's nice, Mom. It's nice.
There's quite a lot of shot
in the pigeon,
so mind how you go
or you'll crack a tooth.
And the shot can take a bit
of feather in, too.
Mm, shot and feather.
Shall we begin with
the negotiation straight away?
(SHIV LAUGHS)
The first time I've had you
in for the night in a decade.
It's just a shame it's so
you can put the squeeze on me
- for your father.
- Ma, it's not like that.
- No?
- ROMAN: No.
Tell me, what does it feel like
being sent here
to wheedle out your mother.
(CHUCKLES) Don't look at me.
I'm not getting involved.
She's right.
Oh. Thank you.
Thank you, a bit of solidarity.
Twenty years too late,
but never mind.
Someone's taking Mommy's side.
If... If you want to get into it,
you're just posturing, right?
And if you go
with Sandy and Stewy,
you're burning down the Coliseum
with your children inside it.
I've thought about it.
I've discussed with Rory.
Yeah, well, great to get
his brain on it.
Potatoes.
He's actually rather clever.
Yeah, before he rolls
one of his tobacco
and hash monstrosities.
- Oh my God.
- CAROLINE: Sorry, what was that?
(MOCK BRITISH) Nothing, Mum.
There's a number.
Ah, here we go. The chiseling
begins. This'll be good.
How much can we screw out
of our dear old mother?
Well, Dad,
unrelated to the vote of course,
is willing to reopen
the divorce settlement.
CAROLINE: So, what's the number?
Well, what do you want?
I want to piss off your father.
Well, I think that's working.
Mm-hm.
Come on, help yourselves.
All right then, come on.
What's his top number?
Well, he told me
to tell you ten, but it's 40.
- So, it's 50.
- N... No, it's 40.
(CHUCKLES) Roman,
you're not very good at this.
No, what's the real top?
- He doesn't have the real top.
- (CHUCKLES)
Dad would never tell him.
I know what I'd like.
Tell him the summer palace.
The Hamptons House.
You hate it out there.
Yeah, but he loves it,
doesn't he?
He loves the parties,
the clam bakes
with people who despise him.
Such fun.
ROMAN: But that's like...
What is that?
That's like 150 million.
It doesn't matter, Roman.
It's just numbers.
I'll have a word
with Jack the Ulsterman, too.
Can throw that in.
- Okay. But...
- CAROLINE: Or...
How about 20 million...
and you kids give me Christmas
every year.
Oh, come on.
Mom, don't make it like...
I would like to come
for Christmas.
Sure.
No... You never invite us.
Well, that's because
you've made it quite clear
- you wouldn't come.
- SHIV: That was one time.
CAROLINE:
That was several times.
- I was 18.
- CAROLINE: Look.
I would like to see you
for Christmas...
instead of you always being
with your father.
Why don't you ask him
what he'd rather?
He can keep the summer palace
if I get the family
every Christmas.
You have to have good lines
of communication
after a divorce.
It's absolutely key.
So, I think we have to hear
which he'd prefer.
Let's make him choose.
♪ (SOMBER MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
- ♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
- (KETTLE WHISTLING)
Y'know, it's a shame
you didn't make it to supper.
It ended up
being rather a nice evening.
I'm sorry I missed it.
CAROLINE: Turned out your father
was prepared to sell you all off
like chattels to keep a piece
of real estate,
but that doesn't surprise me.
You're gonna be okay to come
for Christmas, I take it?
- Uh-huh.
- CAROLINE: Great.
- Hey, Mom. Mom.
- Mm-hmm.
I... I, uh...
have some...
some things I'd like to, um...
to talk about.
To... To tell you.
No more long lists
of my emotional deficiencies.
KENDALL: No, Mom.
No, it's, uh...
It's something I've done...
that I don't feel great about.
Oh.
Right.
Oh dear.
Do you think maybe we can talk?
Sure. Absolutely.
Go ahead, but, um...
Yeah, but are they quite
difficult things? Because...
you know... a bit tired
for home truths.
Right.
Um...
Well, yeah,
it's a bit difficult.
Okay. Mm-mm.
Well... go on.
- It's fine.
- No, no. I want to. Come on.
- KENDALL: It's okay.
- CAROLINE: No.
If you want,
we can absolutely do it now,
but... you know, it might be
better to do it over an egg?
KENDALL: Sure.
Uh-huh. Let's...
Let's do it over an egg.
Yeah. We'll feel better
in the morning,
and we can do it tomorrow.
Okay.
Sleep tight, sweet boy.
Fuck.
Du... Yeah, h... how did it
come to this, huh?
Uh-huh.
- GREG: How did it come to this?
- TOM: You're right.
- What's th...
- You're right.
No one will ever know.
No one will ever know
you sent me to shred the records
of off-book hush-money
and illegal intimidation.
Huh?
- Yeah.
- (CHUCKLING)
Put on the disappearing sauce.
Sauce it. Sauce it.
Okay. (CLEARS THROAT)
A little purifying flame.
- Okay, stand back.
- Oh, yeah.
(LIGHTER CLICKS)
(CLICKING CONTINUES)
Okay, just a minute.
The evidence does not want
to be destroyed.
♪ (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
GREG: Ow! F...
"Oh, Lord of Malfeasance,
give us your divine blessing."
- (CHUCKLES) Hey, hold my beer?
- Hey! Yep.
GREG: Whoa, whoa!
BOTH: (CHUCKLING) Hey!
- Yeah.
- Good!
♪ (MUSIC CONTINUES) ♪
- RECEPTIONIST: Hi, there.
- Hi, uh...
I'm here to see Logan Roy.
Sure, this gentleman
will show you to him.
♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
Hey, Dad.
Siobhan. Oh...
They told me you were here.
- This is unexpected.
- SHIV: Oh.
Yeah, we were due a check-in
with the memo.
And then you fled the country,
then you fled London.
- Well...
- So...
My schedule goes through Kerry.
We've had some emergencies.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, you're kind of elusive,
Dad.
Why didn't you tell me
you were coming?
(CHUCKLES) Uh, well,
because...
honestly, I was afraid that
you would run away again.
I have never run away
from anything in my life.
Can we just... just talk
about the memo?
LOGAN:
Uh, I owe you a response.
Oh, you've not...
you've not read it?
Siobhan, I have an in-tray
the size of Argentina.
Okay.
You know... Actually,
you know what? Also, I...
I need to ask. Is it still me?
What?
Oh, come on! Dad.
Has anything changed? Because,
you know, it feels like it has.
And, you know,
when you said it...
- it felt really real.
- LOGAN: Uh-huh.
SHIV: And I know... I know you
haven't always liked my words.
You haven't always been happy
with my words,
but come on. We can discuss.
LOGAN: Uh-huh.
You know that I want this,
and that I can do it.
Mm.
Then why are you
fucking me about?
As in...
Putting your name in
for the Pierce job?
Mm?
- I...
- Talking to those backstabbers.
- Huh? What's that all about?
- Uh...
If you're gonna be coming
in here
talking a whole load of crap
to your father?
- Who t... who told you?
- LOGAN: Who told me?
It's all over town.
Nan Pierce is shouting it
like a war trophy in the city.
Okay, well, you know what?
I had to keep my options open,
Dad.
Oh. Oh, yeah. I see.
I see. 'Cause we...
'Cause we have a little fallout
or something?
We're a family.
We can have our bumps.
I don't expect that.
- Well, it's not that I was...
- Family, Siobhan!
If you don't understand that...
then fuck off.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Eggy pegs?
She doin' eggy pegs?
KENDALL: She's, um...
She's sorry if she misses
our departure.
- She's got quite a lot to do.
- Mm-hmm.
Sure. Can happen.
Yeah. Yeah, it can. Right.
♪ (THEME MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
LOGAN: There you go.
Hey, Dad. Um, Dad.
- Just need to confirm something.
- LOGAN: Oh.
Decent deal.
Right? 20 and Christmas.
Good kid. Good kid.
Yep, I screwed Mom for you.
That's, you know,
the fucking dream, right?
You should probably go
and poke your eyes out now.
Right. Yeah.
- How'd it go with Shiv?
- LOGAN: We had it out. Yeah.
With the ammunition,
I think I got the noose
from around my neck.
- RHEA: Good. Good.
- Thank you.
I'm pleased to help.
You know, I've been thinking...
maybe... maybe look farther
afield for the next me.
Maybe a shortlist
of two or three?
I'd be pleased to help you look.
(PHONE VIBRATES)
- KENDALL: Yeah.
- SHIV: Hey, Ken.
Listen, is she on the plane?
KENDALL: Uh-huh.
Okay, just...
I think we've got a problem.
Just be careful, okay?
I think I got fucked.
♪ (MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
SHIV ROY: I hear you're putting
some names together
for Dad's CEO search.
Leaning towards someone,
say like me,
who wants to kill you,
or yourself
for a second chance at
a multi-million dollar pay day.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
Mr. Roy. A pleasure
to welcome you home.
CONNOR ROY: How great it is
to celebrate our dad's life.
Shout out to Rhea for planning
a wonderful funeral.
(CHUCKING) I mean, memorial.
SHIV:
We need to call a family truce.
Rhea is dangerous.
We should have a plan
in case Dad does something rash.
KENDALL ROY:
Keep it in the family.
SHIV:
We need to stop her.
I think we share
some similar interests.
♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪