- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
For a number of years there was
an unofficial company policy
on the cruise lines that if there
was a serious criminal incident,
we could minimize the
incident to avoid negative PR.
- Incidents like...
- Theft, sexual assault, murder.
Okay, the bad ones.
Yeah. There's hundreds in there.
All you have to do is
sign out some boxes,
do a little bit of shredding,
meet some lovely guys.
Not a big deal, Greg.
LOGAN ROY: We need this.
Bagging Pierce is the
key to our proxy defense.
Any thought to whom you
might hand over the keys?
I really don't like to
deal in hypotheticals.
Oh, for fuck's sake, Dad, just
tell them it's going to be me.
♪♪
NAN PIERCE: Here we are.
We want to announce the sale and Shiv
at the same time or there's no deal.
That's not quite how I do things.
I could go to 25, but
it would have to be fast.
Then in that case, yes.
(YELLS) That's goddamn fucking right!
Here's to us. Money wins.
So, pilot apparently
says another half hour.
It's just slots, it's, uh, 400 jets
fighting over 100 spaces.
If I find some tech fuck
gets landed before us,
I'm gonna kill 'em. Okay?
- We okay?
- JAMIE LAIRD: On the Pierce deal
they're entrenching on the break fee.
Very, very aggressive.
ROMAN ROY: Well, fuck 'em, right?
I mean, they're empty suits,
they're not gonna walk away now.
LOGAN ROY: Maybe...
Maybe we just give them what they want.
ROMAN: We just give 'em what they want?
Excuse me, Dad, I think
you just had another stroke.
I wanna sign here. Today.
Well, I think the one thing is just,
there could just be a burnout issue
- in terms of the teams...
- No! (SIGHS)
Ken, go. I'm tired.
Impress upon them that I
need this done yesterday.
(LOGAN SIGHS)
KENDALL ROY: Okay.
We've been circling for a fucking hour.
When can we expect something in my hand?
- Imminently.
- Like when?
Soon. For confidentiality,
leak protection,
we kept the circle small.
- Everyone's spread pretty thin.
- It's not fucking good enough.
You're fucking me here.
I'm making good faith
fucking assessments
to my father, and you're
making me look like a hack,
and I will not have it.
Stop sucking each other off back here,
and get fucking on it.
You pour the shit I'm pouring on you
on your fucking minions,
and you ride them.
I don't care. 24 hours, rolling shifts,
crack the fuckin' whip.
Everything you're doing
is fucking bullshit,
and I'm very disappointed in you.
I swear to God, I will fucking fire you
if you keep monkeying around...
Put the fucking snacks away.
I don't wanna fucking hear it!
LOGAN: We've been circling
for a fucking hour.
Tell them we're running out of gas!
♪ (THEME MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
♪ Succession 2x06 ♪
Argestes
- (PHONE RINGING)
- FRANK VERNON: Okay, you.
It's time for that most
magical time of the quarter.
- Audit committee. 10-Q.
- Ah, sounds amazing.
Shiv. Come on. Shadow me, Shadow.
Frank, my dad's a prick. Come on.
Nothing... (LAUGHS) I got nothing.
You know what he promised me.
- And they're all up there.
- I can't get into that.
What, you like this? You
like being left behind?
There's limited attendance at Argestes.
They only have a certain
amount of platinum passes,
- and that's all there is to it.
- (SCOFFS) Oh, yeah, right.
Because it would be impossible
for them to get any more, huh?
It'd mean finding
printers and ink, and...
Inconceivable, right?
This is humiliating for you, too.
(SIGHS) Come on, soldier. Let's go.
Now, I like to recite
Prufrock internally
while we check we're GAAP compliant,
but feel free to use
whatever method you prefer
- to numb the pain.
- No. Fuck this. I'm going home.
- Whoa... What...
- SHIV ROY: I am going home.
- Come on.
- I have shit to do. No.
- I'm making a call on this.
- Your dad asked me
- to take you through this stuff.
- Well, you can tell my dad
I made a decision. Okay?
- Hey.
It's Cruises.
(REPORTERS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(REPORTERS SHOUTING)
Hi.
No, I can't talk, sorry.
Time is what I'm indicating here.
ORGANIZER: Mr. Roy.
- Welcome back to Argestes.
- Thank you.
- Mr. Roy...
- ROMAN: Ah, yes.
- ... welcome back to Argestes.
- Thank you.
Programs, and suggested itinerary.
Oh, itinerary, great.
'Cause I'm really hoping
to get into some...
"Airbus culture hike",
that sounds heart-breaking.
- Thank you.
- ORGANIZER: Enjoy your stay.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Look at you scanning for influence
like a yuppie Robocop.
(SIGHS) So, what are you
rocking for the panel?
Jacket or no jacket?
Uh, right, like I'm gonna
fuckin' tell you, dude.
- Fuck off.
- Okay.
- Strategic advantage.
- Fine. But fair warning,
I'm thinking of no socking it.
Rockin' some horny ankle cleavage.
- Ooh. Scary.
- ROMAN: Mm-hmm.
- I'm scared.
- Yeah, you should be.
Or am I just saying
that to psych you out?
- GREG HIRSCH: Hey there.
- Hey.
- GREG: Hey, sir.
- Hey, excuse me.
- Hey, my Sherpa, what's cookin'?
- Yeah, just, uh... just...
Might've just touched Bill Gates.
Ooh. Hey, did you
check out the acoustics
on my room for my talk?
- I...
- And did you get me
on the culture hike?
And what did I... what
did I get in my chalet?
Did I get the nut and fruit box
or the champagne and paperweight?
Nuts.
Yeah.
But, uh... But the talk venue's great.
Uh, it's the same one as Roman and Ken.
- Oh. Okay.
- Yeah. And, um...
And don't worry about the nuts. The...
The cashews are the size of boomerangs.
(CHUCKLES) Okay.
- So, uh...
- Thanks.
Hey. Nice vest,
Wambsgans. It's so puffy.
Thank you, Roman.
What's it stuffed with,
your hopes and dreams?
Oh, wow. Hiking boots. They're pristine.
Oh. Here we go.
All right. All rise for Pope Big Dick.
Hello, Rhea.
Mr. Roy.
You know what I need.
- Hey.
- Hey there.
Yeah, just to say, um, I don't know how
up to speed you are, uh,
with all of the details,
but, um, just to say
that we're all lined up
for the ATN strategy announcement.
Yeah, same shit.
- Different wrapper.
- TOM: (LAUGHING) Well, I hope
we're not gonna... we're
not gonna go with that,
um, banner, but we...
You know, we settled
on, "We're listening."
- It tested great.
- It tested fine.
Do me a favor.
Is that Sandy Furness?
- Uh...
- Uh, yes.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Well, keep talking.
Keep talking.
- GREG: Oh, yeah.
- Uh, I don't want a bump in.
- Not here, not now.
- TOM: Okay.
Vipers would love it.
GREG: Gladly... We'd be honored
to be your talking partners...
So, basically, the
talk is a celebration of
putting audience input front and center.
And hopefully be really inclusive
and quite changey after recent events,
because ATN Citizen is essentially
very similar but with the option of...
How's he... How's he looking?
Is he healthy?
- GREG: Uh...
- He looks...
- GREG: Not really.
- He looks a little enfeebled.
- Yeah.
- TOM: I'd say.
I heard... I heard, maybe...
maybe syphilis?
- Whoa.
- What? Really?
- Interesting.
- And that's definitely...
You don't really hear much
about syphilis these days.
Very much the, uh...
the MySpace of STDs.
Excuse me, Logan.
I, uh, just spoke to Karolina.
It came through.
They're asking for a response.
Get a room. But slow. No ripples.
A room?
Sorry. Uh, the magazine
contacted Cruises directly.
- Who at Cruises?
- Hello?
Just Florida PR.
Obviously, they thought
they could get someone
who might spew if they
went low on the food chain,
but I had 'em all briefed.
What have they got?
How much have they got?
We don't know.
All they're requesting is
a response on one element.
- Karolina said we had two weeks.
- HUGO BAKER: (SCOFFS) Yeah.
Well, I don't know where
Karolina got that from,
so, I... I cannot speak to that.
Uh, so I have Shiv on
the line, if that's, um...
Uh-huh.
Shiv, you're on speaker.
SHIV: So, what the fuck is going on?
I hear there's a big muck-rake
piece coming in on Cruises?
- KENDALL: Yeah, that's right.
- SHIV: So, what's in it?
HUGO: Uh, we don't know exactly.
SHIV: I'm sorry, who is this?
Uh, Hugo Baker, Senior
Vice President Comms
for Parks and Cruises.
- Hi.
- Wait. Is Dad there?
Does he know I'm on this call?
- I'm here.
- SHIV: Okay, so,
tell me again, how...
how did this happen?
GERRI KELLMAN: Oh, well, we
had a tip off some time ago.
New York Magazine
working on a substantial piece.
They're, um, only giving
us limited allegations
and asking for a response.
Okay, so there's a bomb about to go off,
and do we know what the fuck is in it?
Why do you do this, Dad?
Why do you hoard information?
What you don't know can't hurt you.
Obviously, uh, we are
confident on our position,
regardless of the allegations.
KENDALL: And, uh, this'll drop when?
HUGO: Well, online first,
thirty-six to forty-eight hours.
Um, so, yeah. Not two weeks.
Again, I've no idea
where that came from.
So, this sinks Pierce, right?
If you don't get that
done and signed off
- before this drops, then...
- Can we kill it?
No, you can't kill it. Key.
LOGAN: I've killed bigger.
No, not in the last five years.
Respectfully, Shiv, take a beat.
You're new to this, yeah?
SHIV: Oh, yeah, and
thank fuck for you I am.
This stinks of stale, pale male,
and you need an outsider to advise.
- Cease and desist, right?
- Yes, Hugo. We're on that.
KENDALL: No, we go, how
deep are their pockets,
fuckin' scare the shit out of them.
Yeah, get word around,
our lawyers will go balls to the wall,
say he's super pissed.
Subtext is this is personal,
we're feeling vindictive,
get the senior management
asking where they'll go
- if we bankrupt them.
- SHIV: Dad, cease and desist
and a full-on shit-flinging
freak-out is very high risk,
but we could get them to delay.
Tell them we'll get
into it all with them,
we'll cooperate, play it all out,
- and then stiff them.
- Um, we could offer up
morsels in exchange for postponement?
HUGO: We might be
able to find something,
- maybe out of the studios?
- SHIV: No.
Bigger. Juicier.
- People who are... Sorry.
- (HAND DRYER WHIRRING LOUDLY)
Fuck, I'm sorry.
People who are writing
about cruise abuse scandals
are not gonna be getting
all kissy for a plot twist
- on frat baby two.
- No. Delay is too soft.
SHIV: Dad, ignore him.
Accelerate the deal.
What the fuck do you think
we've been doing, Siobhan?
Well, I have no fuckin' idea, Dad,
because you never tell me anything.
Cave on everything,
get them to at least
sign a letter of intent
before the story breaks, it should hold.
No, Dad, we go for the piece,
we scare them into thinking
what they have isn't solid,
just fuckin' kill, kill, kill.
LOGAN: Ken, you're on that.
Start sprinkling how
fucking unreasonable I am,
Gerri, foot down on the
deal. LOI if we need,
They're half-pregnant.
Let's finish the fucking job
- before this breaks.
- GERRI: Sure, but I have to say
- just legally...
- LOGAN: Now.
I need it now.
What money's floating this year?
You mean for a white knight?
I could see what Roman could scratch up.
- Hmm. Tom?
- Roman's hungry.
All right. Shiv, let's get you out here.
- I need your help on the optics.
- Uh, excuse me?
No. I... I am not flying out to Argestes
to be the face of this.
Then what the fuck are you
doing on the phone, Siobhan?
NATURE GUIDE: So, welcome everyone,
to the Airbus Cultural
and Leadership Walk.
We're gathered here
today with a commitment
to sustainability and stewardship.
So, this place-based
learning today will focus on
creating opportunities
for you to gain the...
- Oh, sh... Tom!
- GUIDE: ... perspective for...
GREG: Sorry, Tom?
- Tom! Hey!
- (GUIDE CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
- Hey, buddy.
- Uh, problem.
Uh, you're not picking up?
- Dude, this is a great group.
- Sorry.
You did good.
It's like I've fallen
into a barrel of deal tits.
- (LAUGHING)
- Yeah. So...
So, there's a thing about your talk.
- Um...
- My talk?
Um, yes. Uh... When it got circulated,
uh, legal and comms
wanted you to be aware that
maybe we shouldn't go with
"ATN: We're listening."
Uh, okay. I mean, I really
do like, "We're listening."
It sounds like... I mean, it
sounds like we're listening.
- No. Sure, it's just...
- Yeah.
It's just, um, there's
apparently, in the EPG
on the set top boxes,
the voice activation
mode, it does, um...
Like, there's a gray area in
terms of our data collection,
so that we are kind of like, uh...
We actually are listening.
We're listening?
It's complicated, but... but, yeah.
It seems that we are sometimes,
uh, listening quite aggressively.
- We're listening?
- Yeah.
But it's just to, like,
maximize the user experience.
But if that was to break,
- maybe...
- Oh, fuck!
So, yeah.
So, the question is, is it a smart thing
for you to be saying, "We're listening",
when we are indeed listening?
Why was I not aware of this?
Well, it's basically
legal, the guy said.
But he didn't wanna
put that in an email,
- so...
- What am I gonna call it now?
I don't know. Maybe, uh...
They suggested "we hear
you." Is that any better?
We tested this, Greg! God damn!
- Yeah, I'd love to. Yeah, yeah.
- WOMAN: Great.
Oh. (CHUCKLES)
Hey. Everything is okay?
Uh...
Marcia.
It's possible that some
things will come out.
Nasty things.
People will say things
about me, about the company.
I might need to know you're with me.
Logan...
when I am with someone, I am with them.
Look at me.
I know who you are.
Hey, Rome.
Hey.
You see that guy?
Asgarov.
ROMAN: Oh, Eduard. Him?
Your dad is intrigued by
sounding out big money,
in the event that the
Pierce deal goes under.
Well, it's a done deal though, right?
Yeah, I don't know.
Could you start a conversation
in case we need an emergency exit?
White knight, go private?
With Eduard?
In his loafers made from
the skin of... I don't know,
what is that? Human rights activists?
- (ROMAN CHUCKLES)
- Uh-huh.
His dad has a hose attached
to the central bank.
He's apparently conceptualising
a 300-year investing horizon.
So, this is what, make-up sex?
This is you grinding yourself against me
and saying sorry for not
telling me about Shiv and Dad?
Roman, your dad wanted
Tom on this. I said you.
Come on, please.
I don't know what the world
is gonna look like in 36 hours.
Just... Just do what you can.
I don't know if it's wise
for us to be seen talking.
Oh, I can take a bit of tittle tattle.
Well, you're an old rhino.
I'm just a flighty, little sparrow.
We'd like to ink it here tomorrow.
Sure, um... I mean,
we appreciate the need for
expediency from your end.
From what I understand, we're
still some distance apart.
The break fee? Oh.
Tell your crowd if
they push, we'll cave.
Undermining your own position?
Could you sue yourself?
(LOGAN SIGHS)
Listen, Rhea.
Uh...
Can you persuade her that if
she doesn't sign here tomorrow,
we might walk?
Later. Uh...
I hear the culture
hike's the hot ticket.
But I'm not sure you're crazy about
either one of those things.
- KENDALL: For tomorrow?
- JESS JORDAN: So, um, 11:00 AM,
we've got Thomas Fisher doing
"Qualities of Inequality".
- What difference...
- Right.
Hey, hey. Look who it is.
Daddy's boy.
I hear your staff are all
killing themselves now.
Yeah, at the thought that
you could be their boss.
Which you never will be.
No, sure, because of
all the acquisitions
you guys are making,
like, really bloating
yourselves up, huh?
There's a 75-dollar Cobb salad here.
Dude, you should buy that,
use that as a defense.
- Yeah. Yeah, maybe.
- Uh-huh.
Either the Cobb salad
or something else tasty.
(LAUGHS) Ooh, that's...
scary. What could that be?
Is it a hamburger? Is it calamari?
Is it fuckin'... Dude, is it Napster?
(KENDALL LAUGHS) Look, I'm
just gonna say, honestly,
we have something coming in,
and it's gonna make your deal untenable.
So...
I thought, as a friend,
I should mention it.
Oh, that's kind.
That's like BFF shit right there.
Look, I'm not fuckin' with you, Stew.
I swear on my children's lives
that right now, we
have a deal in the bag
so big that it's gonna
kill your approach. Okay?
And I feel a certain level of regret
about how things have
panned out between us.
The thing is, Ken,
and due respect...
I really don't trust you.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CAMERAS CLICKING)
So... So, wait a second. So...
So, we're gonna go with, we...
We're gonna go with, "we hear you"?
"We hear you". Yeah.
Are you still worried?
"We're listening", "We hear you"?
It's the same problem, isn't it?
Well, it's maybe less active.
You know, it's... it's
more... Couldn't...
"Couldn't help glimpse
you changing unless, uh,
we put a spy cam in your shower."
"We hear you".
I think it's a problem.
Um, we're... we're
listening, we're hearing you.
I think it needs to be
like, "We're hearing", but...
but nothing that's
gonna bite me in the ass.
Yeah, okay.
- You know?
- So maybe it's like,
"ATN: We're here for you",
and "here" spelled H-E-A-R.
"We're hear for you"?
That's just jibberish.
"We hear for you"!
- Okay. "We hear for you."
- Yeah.
So that might be like,
"We... We... We hear for you,
man, 'cause you don't need
to hear. We hear."
- Yeah, we...
- And also... also,
"we're here for you." Right? Is that... ?
- Yeah. "We're your guys."
- Am I making sense?
It's good, because it's
like, it's not clear exactly
what the hell it means,
- so, lots of wiggle-room.
- Yes.
- "We hear for you."
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Okay. Wamsgans.
- "We hear for you."
♪ ("LAST NIGHT A DJ SAVED
MY LIFE" BY INDEEP PLAYING) ♪
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Excuse me, Eduard. Sorry,
don't mean to be rude.
I'm, uh, Roman Roy.
- Oh. Hey, man.
- How you doin'?
Do you think we can talk for a minute?
Hey. Sorry. Thanks.
So, how you doin' with...
(SIGHS) You know, just walking around,
getting pitched to fuck.
Yeah, huh.
Mm. Mm-hmm.
I hear you're in trouble.
- ROMAN: The proxy?
- EDUARD: Mm.
ROMAN: No. I mean, we're under pressure,
but, yeah, nothing we're worried about.
EDUARD: Hmm.
(SNORTS AND SIGHS)
- ROMAN: Mm. Thanks.
- Right. So...
you wanna hit me up
for my big bag of swag?
Borat the fucking
pipeline piece of shit?
Oh, no. Come on, man.
You're a discerning fellow
that everyone, like... You
know... Are you kidding me?
You're like fucking
Warhol of, you know...
- of, um...
- Of?
- Of? You know where I'm from?
- Uh, Stanford?
- (LAUGHS)
- I mean,
Originally... No, I don't.
I do not know where you come from,
and you know what?
I'm embarrassed about
it. I would like to know.
Man, the shit happening
- in Baku...
- Uh-huh.
I'm serious.
You're laughing at us?
We're laughing at you.
What is it you're, um, bringing to me?
Other than a begging bowl?
ROMAN: Oh, no begging bowl
here. Just, uh, you know,
offering you some, maybe,
investment, uh, opportunities.
You're a fucking news guy, right?
- Mm-hmm. Yeah.
- Why is the news so...
- (PUFFS CHEEKS) You know?
- ROMAN: Yes.
- No, I know... I know.
- Yeah.
It's very... Yeah. I don't
know why the news is like that.
- I hate that.
- We can talk about that.
- Sure. Absolutely.
- Mm.
Yeah, the news with a positive agenda.
A positive agenda for my region.
- ROMAN: Okay.
- Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
But independent. Real stories
we'd fund, but hands off.
- Right.
- Objective.
A hundred percent independent?
But from our point of view.
All right. Yeah. Hey,
that's a really, uh,
really enticing project, yeah.
I'd like to keep the conversation going.
Yeah.
- Oh, great. Good talking to you.
- Yeah.
Oh, sorry. Hey. Hey, uh, big fan, uh...
- of... of all your money.
- Yeah.
GREG: Yeah. Thank you. Hey, hey.
What's going on?
You... You doin' the old cocaine?
(WATER RUNNING)
Could I get... Maybe get a little bump?
Bump? Greg, what happened?
GREG: It's like a power party out there.
Like, tech titans and,
like, supermodels, and...
I just need a little boost.
Okay. Well, good luck with that.
- Dude, come on. Come on. Stop.
- No.
They don't have paper towels.
They've gone all green and shit.
Dude, seriously?
So, all of a sudden,
I find myself in charge
of like a billion-dollar budget,
and it's really exciting.
And it's... And it's...
I thought I would...
You know, I would
suffer from the pressure,
but I fucking love it. I really love it.
- Hey.
- Hey!
Oh, my God. Shiv! What the fuck?
- Nice to see you too, Tom.
- Nice to see you. Hey.
Hey, how are... Why didn't
you tell me you were coming?
It was a last-minute thing.
- Hi. Shiv Roy.
- Pleasure. Nia.
Oh, of course. Yeah,
congratulations on the IPO.
- NIA: Thank you.
- Would you just...
- Could you give us a moment?
- Yeah.
- See you later, huh?
- TOM: See ya.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- But you're here.
- Uh-huh.
- Hope that's not inconvenient.
- TOM: No! No.
No, I'm not being...
No. It... It's nice.
- This. It's just...
- Uh-huh.
You know, you're often...
It's unsettling. I mean, the texts.
Yeah, sorry. It's, uh...
I've just been busy.
Uh, whatever.
There's a potential crisis coming. Um...
(SNIFFS)
There's a journalist
looking into cruises,
and there's a big piece coming.
Okay.
- What?
- We don't know exactly.
- Uh, come here.
- Oh, shit.
Are... Are they scapegoating
me? Is the piece about me?
No, the piece hasn't come out yet.
- No one's read the piece.
- Is this about... No. Okay.
Nothing has happened.
No, we're jamming it up.
I'm just telling you what I know, okay?
Okay. Have I gone red? I
feel like I'm going red.
Suddenly everyone wants me here.
- Gerri called. And Rhea called.
- Right. Rhea?
Yeah. Suddenly I'm everyone's
favorite piece of blast protection.
- TOM: Right.
- Yeah.
- Bullet-proof tits or something.
- So... So what...
what do they want a quote
on? Did they ask for me?
Tom, the piece is not about you.
But there's a trail from...
there's a trail from Mo
to Bill to me. You're safe.
- Which is good, but, uh...
- Yeah.
I'm on the outside.
I don't know anything.
- That's why I'm useful.
- Yeah.
SHIV: Okay.
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- ♪ (MUSIC CONTINUES) ♪
Were you trying to bang Nia Bayton?
TOM: Excuse me?
Nothing.
Well, no. God! No.
- Oh, Shiv.
- Right. Fine.
Shiv.
I mean, I wasn't. But if I was, uh...
that would actually be,
under the arrangement, okay.
You know?
- Tom. I know her.
- Well, you know of her, but...
It would be a bit fucking awkward.
Just use your common sense, okay?
Right, 'cause I might
say that, you know,
spending the night with an actor
in a play financed by your brother
and not telling me for ten days
was a little bit... awkward.
Come on. Nia's a real person.
With a face.
Fine.
No.
Okay.
So, anyway. It's nice that you're here.
Yeah, I missed you.
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
- How'd it go?
- Uh...
He might be good for infinite billions,
but he wants a front news
channel to spew propaganda.
- We into that?
- Um, I guess.
- Depends on the numbers.
- Right.
Plus, the whole... I mean...
Obviously, it's an ethical minefield.
Sure. Of course.
But if we took a position of "fuck it"?
Well, that's an interesting
ethical position.
Silo it off?
Well, what is it? Why's
he got me chasing this?
GERRI: He still hasn't told you?
Pathetic, isn't it?
- I don't know. I can't say.
- Right. Course.
Course not.
You know, right now, if, you know...
If anything happens to him,
you're on the piece of paper
as the next ruler of the kingdom.
Mm. I think I've been made well aware
of how unlikely it is
that will transpire.
Sure. Right. But you know how you're...
so efficient and good at your job?
- Well, thank you.
- But also sort of, like,
invisible? Like wallpaper, like a...
boring old sort of nothing.
Like a competent kind
of clever filing cabinet
that everyone seems
content to have around?
- Uh-huh.
- ROMAN: And I'm like a fucking
- rockstar moron.
- GERRI: Right.
I mean, obviously, these
are our public profiles,
not our true essences.
I have thoughts, but continue.
Well, just floating, like,
is there an angle here,
for a team up?
Like, me, kind of a Jagger-Tarzan,
fronting things up and
swinging through trees
with my little dick,
singing and killing shit,
and you, back home, cooking us soup,
and making sure the
numbers are right. Hmm?
Rockstar and the mole woman?
Wow, you're really selling me.
But it would be chair and CEO.
Or CEO and chair.
And you will get properly "fuck you,
fuck you, I don't even
care about climate change,
I'm in New Zealand with
my own private army" rich.
Not like some pathetic
asshole beach house
on the Vineyard rich.
It's late.
Off you go.
Thanks, mole woman.
Thanks, rockstar.
Night night.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
God. Here I am.
Is he gonna make me take off my shoes?
- RHEA: You slept okay?
- Couple of hours. The usual.
What am I supposed to do with this?
- You wear it, Nancy.
- Oh, absolutely not.
Oh, come on. Join the fun.
A show of false humility.
Everyone wears one.
Zuckerberg wears one.
Hand me a pen and I'll
write my name across my face.
You okay for this?
I think I made my
position perfectly clear,
but for whatever reason you
felt it urgently necessary
to put me in transit
for grapefruit juice
- and a plate of eggs.
- You should go at your own pace,
absolutely, that's imperative.
I just think this is
such a good deal for you.
For... For us.
That it's worth a little haste.
So, we have a little room
for signing right in there.
Just in and out, and boom.
- (LOGAN SIGHS)
- KENDALL: You okay?
Is it the altitude?
I don't know. Maybe.
Um, what... what's...
- What's with the... ?
- Uh, yeah, let's...
- let's move you around.
- No, no. No.
I'm not in a fucking
wheelchair. You don't...
I'm good. I'm good.
- (LOGAN CLEARS THROAT)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- LOGAN: Sunglasses.
- Yeah.
I just had a call from Karolina.
The magazine is not cooperating.
They feel bullied, and
the piece might go up
this morning. Print, Monday.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Well... (STAMMER) When?
How long do we have?
Hours. Maybe minutes. I...
What do we do? Do we bail?
- LOGAN: Hmm.
- KENDALL: Dad?
I'm thinking.
We should leave. We
need to get out of here.
Let's leave. We go. Oh.
Apologies.
Well, I feel like the
belle of the ball out here.
Very discreet.
You're happy with this table?
Visible enough from all sides?
Oh, it's all quite adolescent, isn't it?
So, we're there. Correct?
Happy about the break fee, the rest?
Sorry, did I miss the preamble?
I heard that you were
going to apologise for
your outburst at Ternhaven.
Oh, I... I... Sorry. I'm tired.
Well, that's appreciated.
My dad is just reflecting our desire
to get this concluded as swiftly
- and amicably as possible.
- Mm-hmm. Yes.
Every day a letter, a meeting, a call.
I'm afraid my metabolism
tends a little slower.
We're due a check-in
with the cousins later on
this afternoon.
LOGAN: Yeah, but we can sign.
We are ready to sign.
- Ken?
- Yeah. Uh, right in there.
We thought we could sign and
then have a nice breakfast
- out here.
- But before we do, I...
I think there's perhaps a wider
conversation to be had here.
- Uh-huh?
- We would be interested
in exploring the option...
Uh, I'm sorry. I...
I can't concentrate until I order.
Good God, the prices.
I'll, uh. I'll just have
tap water, thank you.
Um... No, no, thank you.
We would be interested
in exploring the option
of a bonus based on PGM performance.
Of course. We could
cover the legal fees.
Your side, outside counsel.
The whole thing.
Well, this... this isn't really
for us to discuss here, surely.
Well, I think I've explained, uh,
there's a limit to our patience.
Logan, I think perhaps
we're not going to agree
to anything over watermelon.
Well, what's it gonna take?
Why are we still fuckin' around?
I think perhaps we all need
a little less sunshine and vinegar.
It always gets a little testy
at the end. We're all good.
Nan, is there not a way we
could sign the LOI at least?
(CELLPHONE CHIMES)
Dad, I'm wondering if
maybe we should get to
our next appointment?
Oh, yeah, sure. Sure.
RHEA: Why don't you do
that? Let us chew a while.
- Soon.
- RHEA: See you later.
So, what do we think?
It's bad, but not...
(SIGHS) I don't know.
We should have gone at them harder.
Paper copy. Now.
Coming up from reception in two.
Oh, so everyone in the fuckin' world
has read it except me, huh?
Hey. Okay, so where's the link?
Why did no one send me the link?
Just fucking Google it.
Google what? I don't know what we did.
Uh, "Brightstar roller coaster rape."
- Give me something.
- Sending link now.
Thank you. (SIGHS)
Well, fuck me.
Do you think they could make this text
any fucking smaller?
This is pretty gray.
Yeah, but also vivid.
Hey. Great work on frightening them off.
Uh-huh. Good work on stalling.
I'm reading.
- Thanks for coming.
- SHIV: Yeah, sure.
Uh, is everyone here
remedial at reading? Come on.
Is it me or is this bullshit?
Maybe this, maybe that.
- Rome, careful.
- Is this one of those things
that I need a woman to
explain to me why it's bad?
- Shiv? Is it bad?
- Don't fuckin' ask me.
I'm not your grope Geiger counter.
What do you think, Rome?
Um, I do think it's bad, but
it's not that fuckin' bad.
LOGAN: (SIGHS) Fuck.
What's the protein?
HUGO: They found a woman, Keerson.
She was working the cruises
back in the mid '90s,
name-checks Lester McClintock.
She says Uncle Mo asked for sex
with her and the other dancers
to get their contracts renewed.
ROMAN: Were all of you in on this?
Did you all know this was coming?
- It's not ultra-detailed.
- Amazing.
- So they fucked.
- It says sexual exploitation.
Yeah, she's saying that
she was one of the only ones
who refused to sign an NDA
and that we derailed
her career as a result.
- Is that it?
- GERRI: No, look.
The old Hewson story, the woman
that jumped and drowned...
LOGAN: Uh-huh.
... what if something happened to her?
It's... It's just innuendo.
The dancer says that
she heard stories of
dozens of other women who
actually signed the NDAs.
Okay, but in terms of actual stuff?
GERRI: There's not a lot of
specifics. It's spooky words,
you know, data wipes, NDAs, shadow logs,
hiding cruise malpractice.
But cold hard facts, it's
one woman in the 1990s,
not like 20 women four years ago.
Great. I'm glad we're able
to do such good victim math.
Gerri's just saying
it doesn't necessarily
- punch through.
- Sure. But you know...
- this is not okay.
- We know it's not okay, Kendall.
We're preparing a corporate response.
Do we have outside PR?
Pinks passed. We've got J Preston.
SHIV: No, seriously?
They're three disgusting,
old, white dudes.
They'll probably just say
they're money-grubbing sluts.
- It's bad PR to hire them.
- I mean, call me sociopathic,
but doesn't this all seem a tiny bit...
quaint in comparison
to the past few years?
LOGAN: He's right.
It's cultural splash back.
We're being punished
for the sins of others.
No one real gives a fuck.
No, no. We... We can't
be seen to minimize.
I think we need to
loudly and quickly say
that this is not okay.
I think the question is what
closes this down fastest?
Do we say it's something
and we'll fix it,
or it's nothing and fuck off?
Something. There have
to be consequences.
Nope. Condemn and move
on. It's just good advice.
LOGAN: If we get into it all,
they'll never be satisfied.
It's bullshit. It's all about me.
It's not real, it's not honest.
They don't give a flying
fuck for these poor bitches.
They hate me.
So, no! Condemn and move on.
New circus in town tomorrow.
What about the, um, panel? Kendall?
Roman? Do we cancel?
No! Fuck no!
No. Obviously not, no.
- I meant...
- Obviously, it'd be great
if we do go ahead with
it, to, uh, have a person
who could speak to it in terms of...
A woman.
- Gerri?
- Well, not legal counsel.
That gives the wrong sign.
No, I mean... It's
something of a no-brainer.
I... I don't know, I...
- Come on. I just got here.
- Oh, Shiv.
Would you? Please?
Oh, come on. I'm not good
enough for an invitation,
and suddenly this blows up
and you wanna jam it up my...
fucking uterus and smother
it in estrogen? Please.
No, I...
I'm not fully briefed.
We don't need Shiv. I can do it.
We can do it.
Fine. We could do with your help,
but fine.
Okay. Let's get out there.
- ROMAN: Walk of shame?
- Yeah.
Everybody out. Business as usual.
So, you want me to touch base with Rhea,
- take the temperature?
- No, no, no, no, no.
No one speaks to Rhea.
- Me, Laird, no one else.
- GERRI: Right.
Shiv, you're with me.
ROMAN: Little miss
fucking credible, huh?
- (CELLPHONE CHIMES)
- Logan, your 6:00 PM canceled.
- Also, your 7:30.
- Qatari money?
Uh, he said he'd meet for coffee.
Wary about dinner.
And Jack canceled dinner.
Playground bullshit.
Everyone's waiting to
see how it plays out.
- (LAUGHING)
- Hang back a second.
What's up, dude?
I guess if you did
have something going on,
you know, like, deal-wise,
it's kinda, like,
dead in the water now, right?
Like some of the women
that went on those cruises.
Ken, I'm so sorry, bro. I feel for you.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- Hi.
- SHIV: How are you?
- Okay.
- SHIV: Uh-huh.
- You?
- SHIV: Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Good.
Jamie...
- You've seen?
- Uh-huh. Yeah. It's not good.
- LOGAN: No.
- It's not good for the Pierces,
it's not good for the proxy fight.
- I need to speak to Rhea.
- I've tried calling.
Several times.
I'm wondering, in any event,
if I'm the right flavor of
person to be reaching out.
Now my reputation seems to
be a fluctuating currency.
But, uh, young Siobhan,
she's as close to T-Bills
as we're likely to get.
- (GRUNTS)
- Dad?
(LOGAN GRUNTS, RETCHES)
- Christ.
- Oh, my God. Dad.
- Jesus.
- Dad?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. We're fine.
- Uh-huh. We're fine.
- (LOGAN GRUNTS)
- I'm fine. I'm fine.
- Okay. We're fine. Thank you.
- RHEA: Hi.
- Oh, hey.
Sorry I couldn't meet you for coffee.
I've had wall-to-wall meetings.
No, it's, uh... it's fine.
You're hiding from us. I'd do the same.
How's your dad?
The rumor mill is
saying practically dead.
Uh... yes. Fine. It's...
It's the altitude.
Uh, so...
The piece. I'm sorry for all the fuss.
You know how these things are.
No, I... I don't, actually.
Okay. Well, uh, for a few days...
you know, people step away from you
like you farted on the dance floor
but you ride it out. It's no big deal.
Uh-huh. But you're here. Checking in.
Yeah. Well, I was
surprised that you called.
The acceptable face.
Right.
So, you heard the piece was coming,
and you're still pushing this?
You must really want this to happen.
Well, I'm easy come, easy go.
Uh-huh.
And, uh, where is
everybody else's head at?
Well, some of the
cousins are still reading,
which is surprising, because...
they have views on the
new Jonathan Franzen
three days before it
fucking hits the shelf.
(CHUCKLING) Uh-huh. Comfy on the fence?
RHEA: Yeah.
What about Nan?
Um, she's quite unhappy.
- SHIV: Mm.
- She doesn't like a muddle.
Well, I'm around if
she has any questions,
or to allay any fears.
- Sure.
- SHIV: Thank you.
I guess our first question might be
did anyone kill any girls on your boat?
No.
And, you know, statistically speaking,
liners have a high death rate
simply because of the alcohol,
and the profile of the
people who tend to...
Yeah, but the fact that
I'm even having to ask...
Dead girls, boats? Ugh.
It's unpleasant on the tongue.
Well, perhaps the family
would be more comfortable
seeking another source of investment.
I like your dad.
- Uh-huh.
- But...
what sort of a problem
are we looking at here?
Are we in the middle of the storm,
- or is this the first raindrops?
- No, my dad has assured me
that this is not a major issue.
Oh.
Truth is it's in the balance.
Uh-huh.
I think we... they feel that
if it was just a few bad
apples from a long time ago,
then maybe they can grit their teeth.
Well, that's going to be the line,
- so...
- Good.
Well, Nan is coming to your panel,
so I'm sure your flacks
are getting you all
jumping through hoops,
but if you could apply
a nice tourniquet,
then maybe we could patch this up.
Yeah, it's just gonna
be Roman and Kendall.
Right. Roman. Okay. Lovely guys.
- I thought perhaps you might...
- SHIV: No.
No, I'm not, uh, fully briefed. So...
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah.
Could you get briefed?
Uh... I guess.
This isn't really my mess
- to clean up.
- No. Sure.
But... And I mean, I don't
wanna overdramatize,
but Nan gets cold feet
and you can't buy us.
Your dad could lose control. He could.
That's real.
There are many different angles
to me appearing on that panel.
RHEA: Oh, sure. I get
it, honey. But listen.
All I would say is there is a time
to accumulate capital, and
there is a time to spend it.
But hey, whatever. My dad
worked in an asbestos plant.
So...
It's all gravy, right?
And Roman, the safe place
is the three Rs, okay?
- Yeah.
- HUGO: Regret.
It happened a long time ago.
Responsibility.
Belongs to individuals
and not corporations.
Remedy. Super tough, super vague.
The move is condemn and move on. Got it?
- Yeah, got it.
- Okay.
Right, and if you need to smash glass
in case of emergency,
it's enough of that
and back to the session.
Family ownership and corporate
continuity in the digital age.
- Whatever the fuck that means.
- (ROMAN GIGGLES)
- LOGAN: Hey.
- Hey. Uh, so, listen.
I think maybe I should
help out and do it.
- The panel?
- ROMAN: What?
- Yeah.
- Right,
but it's like nine
minutes till show time.
Shiv, no. We already decided.
ROMAN: Yeah. We're all prepped.
Oh, okay, fine. So, send
out the two cover stars
for Toxic Male Monthly, and, uh,
why don't we get Ted Bundy up there,
- make it a three-way?
- Shiv, don't fuckin' pull this.
- Okay? We... We asked you.
- Yeah, and I thought about it,
and I changed my mind.
- What do you think?
- Me?
- Uh-huh.
- HUGO: Um... Well...
- It's difficult.
- LOGAN: Oh. It's difficult.
Oh, I'm sorry, buddy.
Would you like a handjob and an Advil?
Fuck off then.
It's smart.
Shiv works.
It's smart? A sudden,
last-minute line-up change?
Come on, man. It's panicky as fuck.
She's not even in the company.
It looks... kind of fucking cheesy...
- ROMAN: Yeah.
- ... to be honest.
Like, throw our token woman at it?
Well, it can't be two men up
there right now. It just...
It can't. Right?
I mean, if disruption is an issue,
the audience is expecting just Roys,
so, maybe... maybe we
stick at two, and...
someone relaxes.
- Romulus.
- What, pull me?
That looks like a humiliation.
HUGO: Well, we could
just say you got sick.
No. No, you don't bump
me. That's bullshit.
Fuck that. Respectfully,
Dad, why is she even here?
Because I was fucking invited.
No. I need to be out there, okay?
We need to hang tough,
you know? Together. Family.
Oh, okay, so let's just
get Connor down here, then?
- ROMAN: Oh, yeah, get Connor...
- We'll all pile on
so no one's nose gets put
out of joint. Is that...
- That's the important thing.
- I will put your nose
- out of joint
- SHIV: Oh, you should say that
- on the panel.
- That's a funny joke, Siobhan.
If you wanna know what
I really think, I think
you should drop both these
two, and I'll do it solo.
Wow. Someone thinks they're Beyonce.
Pretty desperate, Shiv. You know,
exploiting the situation
for personal gain.
I'm just thinking about
what's best for the firm. Okay?
Oh, sure. Sure. No,
that's, uh... (CHUCKLES)
That's coming through loud and clear.
She's a loose cannon.
She is out of control.
SHIV: Look, Dad. I don't care.
I can make this go away.
I know this in my bones.
I don't need fuckin' flash cards.
I'm not officially in, so
I have freedom of movement.
But if you don't want me,
then I don't give a fuck.
I will go eat lobster and
watch the fuckin' roast,
because it's all...
it's all gravy, baby.
It's important to remember
two fundamental things
about the news.
One: it's new.
All the things that are new.
The many news. The news.
Your boyfriend's really suckin' ass
- out there.
- Two...
Hey, I'm sitting on the
right when we're out there.
You know, I can see your
bra through your sweater.
- Your dick's hanging out.
- Guys.
- There's no way...
- Guys, come on.
- Focus.
- Ro, Ro, Ro.
Do you want me to get a booster
seat for you, when you're out there?
That's hilarious. Your
period just came on.
We aim to evolve our coverage
into something that is, uh...
not only dynamic, but democratic.
And something that truly serves
our audience's ever-changing needs.
And that is why we like to say,
ATN: We hear... for you.
Thank you.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
- Hey. Well done, baby.
- TOM: Good luck. Good luck.
Well?
Afternoon.
Where's Nan?
SALLY-ANNE CORDELL:
Thank you for joining us.
Next up, please give
a warm Argestes welcome
to Roman and Kendall Roy,
joint chief operating officers
at Waystar Royco,
and political and corporate
strategist, Siobhan Roy.
Welcome. You don't do
many of these, Siobhan.
- Uh, no. I'm... I'm hard to get.
- (KENDALL LAUGHS)
I'm exceedingly easy to get.
(SALLY-ANNE CHUCKLES)
So, I love this idea
of corporate continuity
being a positive in the digital age.
But first, I wanted to
give you the opportunity
to respond to the magazine
piece, which came out today.
- Well...
- Yes, well... Uh, go ahead.
No, no. Go ahead.
I mean, uh, I think
the thing for us is...
we don't want to simply
condemn and move on.
You know, we'll... we'll
want to look into this,
investigate it thoroughly,
and then absolutely do the right thing.
Uh, I think we all have
the same view on that.
SALLY-ANNE: Uh-huh
And give us an insight.
Tough day for the company, Siobhan?
Well, uh, obviously I've been, uh,
given the privilege of growing up
around the business,
whilst also being able
to plow my own furrow on the outside.
She's been working in
politics for ten years,
so don't hold out for a straight answer.
(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
Oh, I'll give you a straight answer.
Look, obviously, as you say,
yes, it's been a tough day
for the company.
Sometimes there are, uh...
not errors, not misjudgements
in corporate governance,
- but, um...
- Catastrophes?
Well, no, because it's not really about
corporate procedures here, is it?
It's about human decency
that transcends management structures.
I mean, you know, that's
what's so abhorrent
about these stories
when they come to light,
in whatever sector.
And sometimes it feels like,
"my God, it's... it's everywhere."
Yeah, that... that's absolutely
right. Uh... I mean,
the language... I just would say, um...
Yeah, we don't know.
Right now, we just don't know.
We haven't started the
necessary investigation,
so that language is, uh...
But absolutely, on the sentiment.
I think he's telling me to calm down.
(PANEL AND AUDIENCE LAUGH)
No, no, no. Hell, no. No, I'm not. Uh...
I... You know, if this stuff is true,
doesn't matter to the victim
if these were isolated incidents
that happened, you know,
- many decades ago, right?
- SHIV: Right, and just because
it did happen 25 years ago,
is not a reason to simply
condemn and just move on.
No. No. Absolutely not.
You know, we've been accruing
and maintaining brand loyalty
for decades, and that
trust is a result of
knowing and respecting
- our customers...
- Stop looking around.
You will hurt your neck.
KENDALL: ... to compromise that trust,
we'll take the necessary
steps to make amends.
Uh, we'll do whatever
it takes, you know.
We'll do whatever anyone wants.
You know, it's... it's about
being completely unimpeachable.
And sometimes companies
develop bad habits,
and you need fresh eyes, clean hands,
and new ideas to address those.
KENDALL: Yeah, I mean, that...
that's, uh, the great thing
about a company that's
structured like ours.
We can do that while
retaining core values,
you know, manage change.
- He's good, right? He's great.
- (AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
I think I'm a little more aggressive.
Sometimes I think you just
need a good old fashioned
dinosaur cull.
SALLY-ANNE: And who's the big T-Rex
in your sights?
Oh, no. I mean dinosaur attitudes.
Dinosaur values.
No, I would never go after my dad.
- That's a sport others enjoy.
- (AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
- Hey, Tom. You did good.
- Hey.
Sorry I wasn't there for you before,
but, you know, "we hear for you" now.
(TOM CHUCKLES) No worries.
You fucking shimmered.
- SHIV: Thank you.
- TOM: Was that all okayed?
Nice. Bring your
daughter to the slaughter.
Tell the old dinosaur
what you were gonna do?
KENDALL: Hey, I'm sorry.
"We will do whatever anyone wants"?
- Yeah.
- Fuck it! Right? It played.
It's just words. There
was no press anyway,
so who gives a shit?
- Hey.
- What?
- What was that?
- I was just dancing.
Hey, I'm sorry about Nia last night.
- You can do whatever you like.
- Thank you.
It's not like I really want to.
- Really?
- No.
Because, truthfully, when
I saw you talking to her,
I wanted to smack her
in the face and say,
"Back up, bitch. He's mine."
- (BOTH LAUGHING)
- You should've.
I would've really
liked to have seen that.
SHIV: Oh, yeah? (LAUGHS)
It was too much, Siobhan.
- Dinosaurs?
- Uh...
Yeah. It was over the line.
Shiv went over the line.
Oh, I... I think it was pretty clear
- that I was talking about...
- Oh, no, it was clear. Yeah.
You tortured the old dinosaur.
You barbecued him live, hmm?
Don't fuck with me!
Hey! No! Don't fucking touch him!
SHIV: It's okay. Jesus, Dad.
It played well, okay?
Word is it played well.
- It's okay.
- SHIV: Ro, are you okay?
- (ROMAN SPITS)
- SHIV: Here.
- SHIV: You all right?
- KENDALL: You all right?
Yeah, I'm fuckin' fine.
Fucking leave me alone. I'm fine.
It's just a tooth. I'll get another one.
WOMAN: Ladies and gentlemen,
as it's traditional
to roast us home from Argestes,
it's the Argie awards.
And please welcome your
host for this evening,
Zell Simmons!
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
Hey.
All right. How you doin'?
All right. Look at all you
guys with your blazers on,
coming from Burlington
Coat Factory, huh?
- (AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
- That where y'all shop at?
I'm glad you guys are out here,
solving the world's problems.
I don't see you solving
anything, jerk-off.
Yeah, that's like a guy
sitting on a grain silo
in the middle of a famine, going,
"Why is everybody so down?
- They don't have WiFi here?"
- (AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
Did you talk to Roman? Is he okay?
Yeah. Uh, he said he wasn't gonna come.
But... But he was fine.
All right, who do we got
here? Who we got here?
Oh, we got... The Roys
are here! What's up, guys!
Oh, shit, I hope he doesn't do me.
Ahoy there! Permission
to never fuckin' board?
(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
I think this is going to be a long bit.
I don't understand this tradition.
Why do we come to be insulted?
How is this entertainment?
ZELL SIMMONS: I shouldn't even
be joking about them like that,
because they're in the midst of a...
"hands on investigation".
(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
Yeah, I hear there's a lot
of deals going down here, too.
Man, someone's gonna make a sale.
To Waystar. Hey, I think that's great.
That's like the Hindenburg going down,
and they're like,
"Yeah, hydrogen blimps.
Sign me up!
- That's the future, baby!"
- (AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
No, that's a horrible
idea. It's worse than that,
at least nobody was
forced to give a blowjob
on the Hindenburg!
(AUDIENCE GASPS, LAUGHS)
- Where are you going?
- SIMMONS: Oh, man.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
SIMMONS: Look at Logan Roy,
man. I love that guy, man.
- I mean, he's a very nice guy...
- It's funny 'cause it's true.
Fuck off.
LOGAN: Hey. Hey, Nan.
- Nancy!
- Let's talk later.
Oh, here comes Rhea. Of course.
Oh. Let's talk.
I... I hope you're not swayed by...
I mean, you get these
hothouse atmospheres,
- but we're good.
- NAN: We'll talk.
- We're good though?
- No.
But we can explain.
(SIGHS) Look, it's, uh...
It's a tempest in a tea kettle.
Relax. I drink them by the pint.
(LAUGHS) Oh, thank you.
I am perfectly relaxed.
But if you want to talk about it,
- it's over.
- RHEA: Oh, Nan.
- Come on. Calm down.
- LOGAN: A few bad jokes,
what, and you bend?
I think you're made of stronger stuff
- than these Palo Alto pricks.
- Oh, it's intolerable.
I had a call with the family tonight,
on a number of matters,
and they've left it in my hands.
Which call? After... After our call?
Rhea, may I ask you something?
Have you ever had
any communication or
meetings with Logan Roy
- that I'm not aware of?
- What?
Um... Not...
- Not in terms of...
- Are you trying to figure out
what your attorney would let you say?
- No! I have always acted with...
- I have been rolled.
I have been sand-bagged.
This is a good deal!
You spoke to Logan on the 13th.
What was the nature of that discussion?
I do not recall. It could
have been any number of...
I would like your resignation.
I don't appreciate being hustled.
This is a good fucking deal!
You won't get a deal like this again.
RHEA: It is a good deal,
and I have never had anything in mind
other than what's best for Pierce.
Oh, horse potatoes.
You work for Rhea Jarell.
And as long as our interests
were aligned, it was fine.
You'll be hearing from the lawyers.
Hey. Hey, hey! I haven't finished.
NAN: Good night to you both.
Good riddance to bad rubbish.
You turn this down
and you're fucking your whole family.
Oh, I think my family will be fine,
but thank you for your concern.
- Let's go.
- LOGAN: Hey, wait!
We haven't finished! We
haven't fucking finished!
Do you hear me?
We haven't... Hey! Stop! Stop! Stop!
Do... Fucking... (SCREAMS INCOHERENTLY)
Stop! Stop!
♪ (MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
(DRAMATIC INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC)
TOM WAMBSGANS: We need to end this now.
The copies? I want them.
Well in case things
were to turn nasty...
They're not gonna turn nasty.
No one's gonna break your legs.
Yeah.
Okay, well that feels a bit nasty.
The Pearce pursuit has played badly.
A significant chunk
of stock is wavering.
Caroline.
I need her 3 percent.
I think we've got a problem.
KAROLINA NOVOTNEY:
They're saying you punched him
which caused him to drive
his car into the river.
ADVISOR (ON PHONE): How about
we offer a visit to the family?
GERRI KELLMAN: It might be
time to start getting worried.
LOGAN ROY: I've never run
away from anything in my life.
♪♪
LOGAN ROY: Let's finish the fucking
job before this breaks.
Shiv, let's get you out here.
- I need your help on the optics.
- No.
I am not flying out to
Argestes to be the face of this.
Then what the fuck are you
doing on the phone, Siobhan?
♪ (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
This episode is set in Argestes,
which is like a media
and money conference,
and there's just deals,
deals, deals, deals everywhere.
Might have just touched Bill Gates.
JESSE ARMSTRONG: And all
these massive mega deals
happen in these kind
of weird ski lodges.
So we always felt it would be
an interesting place to set an episode.
Maybe we shouldn't go with
"ATN: We're Listening."
Oh, okay.
ARMSTRONG: Seeing Tom and
Greg down by the waterfall
and outside the movie
theater as they discuss
this unfortunate information
they find out about
what the company EPG has been doing.
There's a grey area in
terms of our data collection,
so that we are kind of like...
We actually are listening.
You know I come from a
comedy-writing background
and there's something
very comfortable for me
about seeing two very able
comic performers do a bit.
- We're listening?
- Yeah.
But it's just to like
maximize the user experience.
But if that was to break, maybe...
Oh, fuck!
The Roys are here.
Permission to never fucking board?
(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
When a scandal hits, you quickly take on
a different set of values
and a different perspective
which is able to distance yourself
from the misdeeds itself.
It's cultural splash back.
We're being punished
for the sins of others.
Logan himself, in the
teeth of a proxy battle,
everyone has that straw that
breaks the camel's back...
- You tortured the old dinosaur.
- The tipping point.
ROMAN ROY: You barbecued him live.
It's not like the most
violent attack in the world,
but there's something about
the suddenness and the ferocity,
and the surprise...
and I guess that it's
misdirected, you might say.
He was angry, not with
Roman, but with Shiv.
And the fact that
Roman gets it might be
an interesting observation
about the way anger
and frustration rebounds
around inside a family.
It's a tempest in a tea kettle. Relax.
I drink them by the pint.
It's over.
LOGAN: Hey, hey, I haven't finished!
ARMSTRONG: I think in that
moment, you see Logan's fear.
At a certain point, people walk away,
and that point, I guess,
is what's intriguing to us.
What is too much?
'Cause the world is tough
and the world is grubby,
and you end up having to bend yourself
to people around you.
When do you decide that
you're bending too far,
and you're starting to
corrupt something inside?
It's an interesting question.
♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪