Well, we need to locate
all written information
relevant to this investigation.
Are you aware of any
document destruction?
You know what? I really need to pee!
I'm gonna have to fight now for
every fucking shareholder vote.
Coochie-fucking-coo.
Yeah, I haven't seen him
like this for a while.
You wanna stay over or what?
RHEA JARRELL: Isn't now the
time to just let him know
you have options?
I happen to know
there's a media operation
in need of a new CEO.
Uh, me? At Pierce?
KENDALL ROY: Have you seen this?
They're saying you punched him,
which caused him, in effect,
to drive his car into the river.
HUGO BAKER: How about we
offer a visit to the family?
Actually, Ken, why don't
you come in with me?
We should stick together on this.
Don't you agree?
Dad? I need to ask, is it still me?
You know that I want
this, and that I can do it.
Then why are you fucking me about?
The Pierce job.
Hey, Ken. I think we've got a problem.
♪ (THEME MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
(TAPPING ON GLASS)
We want to thank you for
coming to this first preview
of Willa's baby,
'cause it isn't easy to...
to give birth in front
of a thousand people.
So... anyway.
Uh... But I... I have to say, I could...
- watch it all day.
- (WILLA CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY)
CONNOR ROY: And if you're
talking with your friends,
remember, a lot of the lines
you heard were placeholders.
- Correct?
- That's right, yeah, um...
I... I had a virus, so...
(CLEARS THROAT) Yeah, I think it's like,
maybe 30, 40 percent improvement
when... if I, you know,
get to full... power.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Yeah, but the cast, amazing.
- (APPLAUSE)
- CONNOR: Absolutely.
But previews, so, you
know, watch this space.
- WILLA: Thank... Thank you.
- CONNOR: Thank you.
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
- (SUCKS TEETH) Fuck.
- You okay?
SHIV ROY: Yeah, just Rhea.
She's like fucking knotweed.
Dad's plaque thing.
Oh, yeah, the little Dundee dinner.
- Trip to Scotland, 50 years in the biz.
- SHIV: Mm.
Yeah, not so little anymore.
She went full on.
She's turning it into a
fucking surprise party,
Rhea-produced Logan-athon.
I would tell your dad that
she's a traitorous viper
and that she stabbed you in the back.
Oh, come on.
Go whining to Logan?
Come... I need to be smarter than that.
- Hey.
- SHIV: Hey.
(BREATHES SHARPLY)
- (INHALES DEEPLY)
- TOM WAMSGANS: Who's that?
Huh?
Is that... "him"?
- Him who?
- "Him who?"
- Look at you.
- (SHIV MUTTERS)
- SHIV: What? No.
- Are you sweating?
It's construction sand,
and it's supposed to be desert sand.
- I mean, can we fix that?
- Sure.
Willa. Hey.
- WILLA: Hi.
- I just want to say congrats.
I didn't realize, but
that was, uh, you know?
- You're a playwright.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Thank you. Yeah...
- Yeah.
I mean, I've always told
you I'm a playwright.
Yeah, but, you know, Roman's, like...
"written a screenplay".
- Thanks, bro.
- Yeah. Yeah.
This is the worst it'll be.
It can only get better.
Right, okay.
KENDALL ROY: Hey, so,
Con, who... who's, um...
Who's that chick that
Willa's talking to right now?
Oh, Jennifer? Yeah, she's one of 'em.
She's one of the wackjobs, the actors...
but no, yeah, she's fantastic.
She's just got this
unbelievable gift for...
- pretending.
- She was amazing.
Oh. Uh-huh. You okay?
Hey, I'm drowning in pussy
and everything's golden.
Well, that's great, Kenny.
- Hey, uh...
- Hey.
- Ken.
- Yeah.
Did you get this email from
Rhea about the tribute videos?
- Ooh, uh-huh.
- Yeah, and you know that she's...
she's lunching Sid and Laird, right?
KENDALL: Mm-hm.
SHIV: I mean...
Shiv, look. It's all
changing all the time...
- Oh. Oh, okay. So, you're like...
- So, like,
- you're out of the game...
- no big deal.
...and you're just
stockpiling lentils and...
- and hoarding antibiotics?
- No, that's not what I'm saying.
I'm just saying it's all good, you know?
It's like there's nothing
new under the sun.
Sorry, will you excuse
me for just a moment?
My father has always
been my greatest champion
and my hero.
Congratulations on 50
years at the top of the biz.
I love you, Dad.
Nice. Uh... You want to try one more?
(CLICKS TONGUE) Why?
No, uh, that was perfect, uh, just...
didn't know if... if you...
you wanted one more.
If it was perfect, why
would I want one more?
I just... I meant, um...
Why don't we do just one more where...
maybe you really, like, sell
how... how you're feeling?
Yeah. Okay. Let's do it.
All right. Take four.
(IN CARTOONISH VOICE)
What up, prick licks?
It's me, Dr. Moron.
I'm a ding-dong, doodle-bug
dipshit with a tit mouse dick
and my dad hates all of you.
Fucky-go-bye-bye. (NORMAL
VOICE) How was that?
Was that good?
CONNOR: It's interesting
that Dad's agreed
to go back to Scotland
for this dedication dinner.
- Yeah.
- CONNOR: He didn't have it easy.
Mm-hm.
He had to shit outside, right?
Sometimes, I think I'll
never truly understand Dad
until I shit outside.
I doubt that squatting
over a storm drain
is going to crack the case on him.
I just said, "I love you, Dad",
like ten times in a row.
I think that doubles my lifetime count.
Hey, what do you reckon,
Rome, Dad boning Rhea?
ROMAN ROY: Can't wrap
my head around that.
Too steamy. Too hot.
We should all talk
about what this means...
for us, you know?
We're... You know, we're
all sensing a shift, right?
(COFFEE POURING)
Well, Gerri says she
looks like the new thing.
CONNOR: Well, it happens
Gerri was the new thing once.
- CONNOR: Remember?
- SHIV: Huh.
You think he ever boned Gerri?
I don't know.
I just think we need to be careful.
Aw, what's wrong?
You all wedgied up because
Rhea stood on your back
and worked your arms like an elliptical?
(CONNOR AND ROMAN LAUGH)
I'm just saying, I wonder
if we should have a plan,
you know, in case Dad
does something rash.
Connor, we're ready for you.
CONNOR: Oh. Okay. Wish me luck.
Hey, Dad. It's me, Connor Roy, your son.
I just want to say that you've
always been my superhero, Dad.
You fight the bad guys
and you always win.
I know we don't get to spend
as much time together
one-on-one as we'd like,
and that makes me sad,
but I'm unbelievably
proud to be your son.
I super love you, Super-Dad.
Hey, what's up?
(LOUDLY) Hey, how are you? Loud!
- What?
- And you're wearing the same clothes
as yesterday. You want us
to think you got laid.
- Nice try.
- (KENDALL CHUCKLES)
- CONNOR: Hey, Ken.
- KENDALL: Hey.
Siobhan's planning to kill Rhea.
Uh... No. I'm not.
We're having a discussion.
There's no plan.
I'm just encouraging us
to assess our options.
Okay. Is that our business?
The business with our name
on it, is it our business?
I don't know. If... You
know, if Dad's into it...
Like, whatever he thinks
is usually pretty on target.
Okay, well, I think Rhea is dangerous,
and I think we need to stop her.
Well, it... it's clear
you need to stop her.
What if she sells the company for parts?
Eight weeks ago,
Dad was ready to kick over
the whole sandcastle...
ROMAN: He didn't though, did he?
Struck a little deal on
the side instead, Shiv.
All right. You know what?
We need to put feelings aside
and call a family truce,
because we need to fuck her
from 100 different directions
at a thousand miles
an hour. I'm serious.
Uh... Kendall.
Yeah, I mean, I guess...
it would be nice to
keep it in the family.
ROMAN: Oh, Ken. Maybe tell
that heartwarming story
about how you tried to kill
him and take over the company.
That ought to moisten the old peepers.
So, Connor, I, um...
Do you know the sand that's in Sands?
You mean the nine metric
tons of Gypsum white
they gouged me for 5.29 a bag?
Sure, I know the sand.
So, I was sitting pretty
close to the stage,
and so, I... I had great seats,
and, um... and I think there's
something maybe living in it,
like per... perhaps
thriving in the sand,
uh, like sand mites, maybe?
I know nothing about that and
bear no legal responsibility.
You'll have to talk
to the sand supplier,
like everyone else.
GREG HIRSCH: Yeah, that's
cool, that's cool, um...
(GREG SIGHS)
Three thousand miles
to pose with signage.
Thank fuck I'm not busy.
You could still cancel.
LOGAN ROY: No, no, no.
Rhea's smart on this.
A little dinner, push 50 years
experience, 50 years growth.
Stress the experience. History.
A platform on which to make
a strategic announcement.
Logan.
Before we settle in,
um, there's a small matter we
wanted to make you aware of.
Uh-huh.
A former cruise employee,
James Weissel in accounting,
uh, so quite inside
the payments and so on,
seems to have gotten
spooked by a lawsuit,
and seems like he
might be about to talk.
I thought we had this all sewn up.
- I said I hoped...
- (YELLS) Don't... interrupt me.
You told me this was all sewn up.
Why am I only hearing about this now?
He was across the
Caribbean '90s situation,
the payouts and all
the other operations.
And then he went up the ladder.
He knows about the shadow logs.
He supervised a number
of "Mo aftermaths".
Okay. Okay. Give him the storm warning.
Get rat-fucker Sam to give him the talk,
"We have endless resources.
We will destroy your life."
- Who knows?
- Kendall, Karl.
- Rhea?
- No. Nope.
Good.
I really don't want this
shit in my ears, you know?
Figure it out.
(SCOFFS)
SHIV: So, Rhea really took the reins
on this weekend planning, huh?
Yeah. She's been very active.
Well... (INHALES SHARPLY)
Must be tough for you, though.
How so?
I just...
I know how he can be when
he has a new enthusiasm.
Don't worry about me.
I'm not a child.
I don't piss on the carpet
every time it thunders.
I just think we share
some similar interests.
I mean, is it okay to let
her do this much planning?
If she wants to throw
him a big surprise party,
who am I to spoil it?
♪ (MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
Ah. (CHUCKLES) The bandstand.
- What happened there, Pa?
- Huh?
Oh... uh, different things.
Yeah, a lot of, uh... Yeah. Hey.
You and Ewan were lucky
to make it out to Canada.
(GROANS) Wasn't such a fucking
hootenanny there either.
Nah. This place...
I look around and... I don't know.
We came back for, um...
when my mother died,
but it was all so... complicated.
You can't explain it.
It's not what you think.
You look at the old pictures
and they want you to think
it's all so fucking simple,
but it was... well, it was...
(SIGHS) It was, um...
I don't know what it was.
It was, um...
(SIGHS) It wasn't...
what they say, you know?
Tell us a story, though.
- Story?
- Yeah, from back in the day.
Oh, yeah?
What, you want a bit about,
uh, old fucking Rosebud?
Rosebud is a dollar bill.
It's whatever it took to
get me the fuck out of here.
Good story, Dad.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
HOTEL MANAGER: Madam.
Mr. Roy.
A pleasure to welcome you home.
Oh, I don't recall people
shedding a tear when I left,
- but thank you.
- Thank you, sir.
Hello.
- HUGO BAKER: Hello, Rhea.
- RHEA JARRELL: Hugo.
- Thank you for organizing this.
- Great to see...
Oh, my pleasure.
So, are you a person who, uh, can't look
someone in the eye
after you've fucked them?
I acted in good faith.
(CHUCKLES) Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I mean, that's what's truly scary,
'cause I think you believe that.
What, do you outsource your fuckery?
You got the right brain
for your TED Talks,
- left brain for your killings?
- That's very unfair.
(SCOFFS, CHUCKLES) Oh,
well, I feel bad now.
I put you forward to Pierce,
and it got out of hand.
Your dad obviously felt out of the loop
and it wasn't as I intended.
Yeah, I hear you're
putting some names together
- for Dad's CEO search.
- Uh-huh, various individuals.
Including yourself?
Well, the pool is small
for this type of position.
Oh. Yeah. Wow. What a surprise.
He needs someone
before the shareholder
meeting. You know that.
SHIV: Yeah, and I wonder
which way you're leaning.
Who's catching your eye to recommend?
You leaning towards
someone, say, like me
who wants to kill you,
or... yourself,
for a second chance at a
multi-million-dollar payday?
I'm intrigued. Keep me posted.
So, are you hearing
anything majorly major
about big shit or whatever
through the shit-vine?
In what sense?
In the sense of the
little blonde goblin.
Is she about to gobble up all the power?
(DOOR LOCK BEEPS)
(SIGHS)
So, um, Frank is concerned.
He says this feels like something new.
ROMAN: Yeah, but he does this, right?
Dad. I mean, remember when
he bought that chick a harp?
Oh, Sally Anne?
She didn't even know how to play it.
This is something else.
He's losing focus.
Out to dinner four nights a week.
The shareholder vote
is going to be close.
If the board gets replaced,
it'll be a clean sweep.
- We could do with options.
- Mm-hmm.
I've made sure that Eduard is invited.
Could you seduce?
(CLOCKS TONGUE) Uh... I don't know.
Do you find me seductive?
I can give him a rim.
- I could rim with vim.
- Could they take us private?
Hmm. They want us to open up
a propaganda news operation.
GERRI KELLMAN: It's that serious, Roman.
We get the money, boom.
Much less oversight.
ROMAN: Hmm? Okay. Well, I will...
I will talk to him, then.
Oh, and, um, one more thing, real quick.
Should we... get married?
What?
You know, not that. Like, an equivalent.
Uh... A thing, like I abduct you
and force you to live with me.
Uh... That's not equivalent.
Well, then, you kill me,
you chop my dick off,
you know, something.
I'm kidding but you
know what I'm saying.
Uh... You eat me, I eat
you, like they do in Germany.
Anyway, lot to think about,
I get it. So, let it...
Bye.
(PHONE RINGING)
- Hey.
- KENDALL: Hey, so,
it hasn't worn off, right?
Like, that was a century-defining fuck.
- Who is this again?
- KENDALL: Jennifer, Jennifer.
All right. So, what
are we going to do here?
I feel like we should
maybe buy an island,
put in a giant island sized bed,
and just make love all day.
(LAUGHS)
You ever been to Dundee?
You wanna come to Dundee?
What about my play?
The play? Uh...
I mean, it's, like,
two nights off. Come on.
It's not Arthur Miller, right?
And, uh, I kinda own a movie studio.
Um... Where is Dundee?
How about you look it up on your phone
on the way to the airfield,
because I'm sending you a driver
and I'm getting you a jet
ride over here tonight.
LOGAN: Oh, the tap water
used to taste sensational.
- It's changed.
- Mm-hm.
MAN: Mr. Roy. You have a second?
- LOGAN: Oh, sure.
- MAN: Transportation to the streets...
RHEA: Marcia, you look lovely.
MARCIA ROY: Oh, thank you.
Uh... So...
I have something I wanted to ask you.
RHEA: Uh-huh.
Are you regularly tested for
sexually transmitted diseases?
Excuse me? (CHUCKLES)
He and I still sleep together.
I don't know what he tells you.
I'm sorry, I... I don't know
what you're talking about.
So, I will be more relaxed
to know that you are clean.
I don't know who else you're screwing.
This... This isn't
appropriate to... to talk of...
- of... of... Like...
- Listen..
I have fought and I have lost,
and I have fought and won,
but when I lose,
the other one will generally
lose an eye or a soul.
LOGAN: Hey, uh, sorry.
Sorry, Marcia, uh,
could you give us five,
just before drinks?
Of course. Thank you, Rhea.
(LOGAN SIGHS)
Everything okay?
What's the latest?
Sure. Uh-huh. All good. Honing in.
Uh-huh. Oh, good. Good.
I mean, thank you for taking
the lead on the little dinner,
all the politics and,
you know, what-not.
Well, I'm pleased to help, but
I'm sensing some turbulence.
Uh-huh.
Shiv.
Oh. Shiv. (CHUCKLES) She runs hot.
She makes boogie men
out of the clothes she
dumps on her bedroom floor.
Always has.
Well, just as long as you
don't mind a bit of feedback.
A few noses are out of joint.
Strong French feelings.
I'm worried I might get
blinded with a baguette.
ROMAN: Just say Rhea beats her
dog or boyfriend or I don't know.
SHIV: Uh... Dad would love that.
The thing you think is ammo is not ammo.
We need to be clear, direct,
with a line of attack.
You know, "liberal, duplicitous".
"She's a two-faced snowflake
with cum on her dress."
Tell her to ask about Rose.
- (CHUCKLES) Oh, shit.
- ROMAN: (HIGH-PITCHED) Yup!
This sounds schemey. Redolent of thwart.
Yeah. How do you feel about
oozing a bit near Rhea?
Just, you know, sorta...
Sorta what?
Well, you know, get... get a bit giggly.
Work it. But so that my dad can see.
I mean, it doesn't kill
her, but everything helps.
ROMAN: I have this idea that
maybe Rhea can mention in a toast.
- KENDALL: Lob a little grenade?
- ROMAN: Yeah.
Are you pimping me out?
- No, no. Nothing crazy, Tom.
- (TOM HUFFS)
Just make her laugh.
Work the arms a bit.
Have a bit of elbow sex.
The woman who my terrifying
boss is obsessed with?
You want me to flirt with her?
Tom, come on. Not...
Not dirty flirty. Just hurty flirty.
♪ (SMOOTH LOUNGE MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
SHIV: Kendall, you
ready to wind up Rhea?
- Did you fuck with her?
- Yeah.
Let's try Rose out on her.
See if she gets a clip on the ears.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- Hey, this is great. It's great.
- Yeah, um...
Yeah... (STUTTERS) Do you...
Do you think it would be
okay if I made a little toast?
I mean, I don't want
to piss anybody off.
Yeah, absolutely.
You could, um...
You could toast his mother, Helen.
- RHEA: Oh, right.
- KENDALL: And, uh...
I don't know, maybe mention Rose,
his sister Rose who
is no longer with us.
He might appreciate that.
- (WHISPERS) Thank you.
- KENDALL: Yeah, sure.
- (TAPPING ON GLASS)
- ♪ (MUSIC ENDS) ♪
Evening, one and all.
I know I'm the new nut in the trail mix,
but, um... (CHUCKLES)
I just wanted to thank you
all for joining, and to...
congratulate our
implacable plaque unveiler.
And, uh, given tomorrow's honor...
let's raise our glasses to those...
who are with us tonight in absentia.
- Logan's mother Helen.
- ALL: To Helen.
And his sister Rose.
So... cheers, everyone. (CLEARS THROAT)
- ALL: (SCATTERED) Cheers.
- CONNOR: Slàinte mhath.
- ♪ (MUSIC RESTARTS) ♪
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
TOM: This is some lunch.
ROMAN: Everybody's
offended by everything.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Wow. Well done. Look at
you, fitting right in,
like a camp counselor
in my butt when I was 12.
Is that Keats?
Anonymous.
I see your thing.
It's good. It works.
You're kinda like a peppy,
fun-gun set to "MILF",
with like, a...
Lean In, woman-y branding
thing that works well
with the Fitbit-moron-whatever people.
I'm a sort of butterfly in the ointment:
colorful but wriggly.
I could see us collaborating.
Oh, yeah? Yeah, you can see that?
Yeah, buttering up the old dunce, huh?
- Nice work. Fuck off.
- No.
- I get your rep.
- Mm-hm.
RHEA: Some labels take
a while to peel off,
but I happen to think you
have the best instincts
of all of them.
Well, bullshit, but thank you.
TOM: Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, this is where the
party's at. Look at us,
all the cool and the
beautiful people in one spot.
(RHEA AND TOM CHUCKLE)
This is like the VIP area, right here.
Right? It should be, like, cordoned off
with, a... like, a velvet
rope, a bit of VIP bondage.
- (CHUCKLES)
- WOMAN: Oh, my goodness.
Hey, Pa, so, listen.
- Uh... The play...
- Yeah, I'm sorry that we, uh...
- we didn't, um...
- No worries.
No, it's just costing
a pretty penny and...
a few financial worries
starting to bubble.
- Be good to chat.
- Yeah, don't worry, son.
I'm sure you'll work it out.
Uh... So... So, Rhea, where's,
uh... where's home for you?
Home was all over.
And did I hear that your
mother... Is this true,
she volunteers for the
Democratic Socialists?
TOM: Oh, my! God, folks, watch out,
we've got a libtard in the punch bowl.
(LAUGHTER)
Quick, hide your pay stubs
before she takes more federal.
(LAUGHTER)
Uh... Yeah, we don't see
eye to eye on everything.
Oh, right.
Oh, uh, I'm sorry, none
for her. She doesn't drink.
RHEA: Um...
Well, I, uh, sip.
But... But... N... No, not really, no.
Oh. Yeah. Sorry, I...
RHEA: Well, not a great deal. Um...
I'm pretty sure, maybe just a drop
if you can fit it in there.
(LAUGHS) For a toast.
(TAPPING ON GLASS)
Ding. Ding. Ding. Ding.
- CONNOR: Well, here's a toast.
- RHEA: Oh. Great.
CONNOR: I guess I just
wanna say how great it is
to have everyone we know
and love in one place
to celebrate our dad's life.
- SHIV: Yeah. Hear, hear.
- ALL: Hear, hear.
Shout out to Rhea for
planning a wonderful funeral.
I mean, (CHUCKLES) uh... memorial.
No, uh, evening.
RHEA: Oh, please...
It's my honor to salute a man...
who will one day bury us all, no doubt.
- KENDALL: Hear, hear.
- CONNOR: Happy days.
- TOM: Hear, hear. Cheers.
- SHIV: Cheers.
ROMAN: Cheerio, Dad.
SHIV: (SIGHS) To Dad.
I have one in my backside.
TOM: Just don't scratch it.
Oh, God. I feel like it's
weirder with one protester.
Like, you don't know whether
to make eye contact, or...
TOM: Well, he really went with
the first draft on that one.
Still, to be fair,
it's pretty effective.
GREG: Apparently, it's
less offensive over here.
It's like calling someone a buddy.
ROMAN: Look at this
shit. Are you kidding me?
If this place was in Brooklyn,
it'd be worth five mil, easy.
This is, like, fine.
- CONNOR: It's totally fine.
- ROMAN: Yeah. Yeah.
CONNOR: I'd live here.
- CONNOR: I mean, I wouldn't but someone could.
- (TABITHA LAUGHS)
TABITHA: I mean, you told
me he lived in an open sewer
and was raised by rats but this is...
Yeah, you should go peek in that window.
That's for sure a bathroom.
And this fucker is pre-war.
There's no way Dad shat in a bucket.
GREG: This stuff's making it worse.
And I feel like this
stuff is attracting midges.
My sand mites are
getting bitten by midges.
Just stop.
- I'm just uncomfortable in my skin right now.
- Just stop.
TOM: Oh, here we go.
♪ (MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
MARCIA: Has it changed much?
Yeah... Everything.
What's he doing?
Okay. There it is.
What am I supposed to do?
I think maybe a photo.
They've said you can go in.
No. Thank you.
Let's go.
- GREG: Wait. Wait.
- SHIV: What the fuck?
Ah. Memories.
Uh... (CLEARS THROAT)
So, I have an update.
SHIV: Oh, yeah?
James Weissel. We don't
really want to bother your dad.
- We know he's enjoying this.
- (SCOFFS) Oh. Uh-huh.
There's a call, and we
might like your input.
- GERRI: That okay?
- Yeah.
So, we made the threat/offer
to Mr. Weaselman.
Five rising to ten.
But he said no.
He said no to ten? Why
would he say no to ten mil?
I don't know, playing hardball?
We need this to go away,
- so I'm gonna double the offer.
- SHIV: Yeah.
Anything to get him to roll, right?
Yeah, right. Sounds smart.
Okay. So, I just wanted to let you know.
Nice to keep your dad in a good mood
for the festivities.
Absolutely.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
Mr. Roy. So happy you could make it.
Well, let's see what my
money bought, shall we?
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
- Everything's state of the art.
- LOGAN: Hmm.
Inking, web-offset press.
We like to say,
we've got a better set
up than most UK papers.
Wow.
A whole school for how to
intern at a clickbait aggregator?
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
"Ten reasons why you're
never getting paid."
(CHUCKLES)
I'm sorry, I have to ask.
Why are you trying to fuck me?
Trying to fuck you? What do you mean?
Rose. We both know what that was.
If anything, I'm just, uh,
mildly offended on behalf of
my sister and Frank, Gerri.
And I wonder about the optics, but, uh,
hey, my dad knows, so...
- Yeah?
- Even so.
I don't know how
you've done it, frankly.
What with everything
you've been through.
Uh-huh.
You're good, though.
(SCOFFS) Right.
- Thank you.
- No.
You're good,
but you're still in the
rock tumbler right now.
You're not ready.
I'm good.
I mean, I'm over my shit.
And I've met someone new.
I mean, she is fantastic.
And, uh, so, yeah, I'm...
I'm not in the place you think I'm in.
No, it's okay.
But when we're out on the
other side of this all...
it's you.
RHEA: I'm telling you
now. It's always been you.
Well...
thank you.
I don't know about that, but thank you.
(APPLAUSE)
Um... They're asking if
you want to stay for lunch.
Fuck, no.
I'll be sure to feed that back
to them. "Fuck, no". Got it.
Ah. Look who made it.
Are you going to change the
name of the airport, too?
As you fly off?
Marcia call you?
EWAN ROY: No. Your new one.
Oh, right.
The Logan Roy School of Journalism.
What's next?
The Jack the Ripper
Women's Health Clinic?
You, uh, had a poke around the town?
I've seen enough.
You've been spreading your
name all over this place
like it was graffiti.
They tried to get me to
go into the old house.
Another plaque.
I saw a mistle thrush at the bandstand.
(LAUGHS) Sure, you did.
- Oh, this old bastard.
- (EWAN LAUGHS)
LOGAN: I used to keep a
log of the birds I'd see.
Your grandpa would go through it
and scrub out the ones he
didn't believe I'd seen.
You were always fairly
generous with your sightings.
(PHONE BUZZING)
- Yeah.
- AUTOMATED VOICE: Hello, valued shareholder,
you will soon have a critical
- decision to make...
- LOGAN: What the fuck is this?
... regarding your
investment in Waystar.
(PHONE BEEPS)
They're fucking robocalling me now.
I was gonna say, it's
nice to see you and, uh,
and the old brother having a chat.
Yeah, well...
GREG: Yeah, he's a tough old bird.
- But... But he's, uh... he's...
- He's morally bankrupt.
He's a nothing man who may well be...
more personally responsible
for the death of this planet...
than any other single human being.
He also makes the Kalispitron franchise,
which is, uh, you know,
solid, mediocre entertainment.
In terms of the lives that will be lost
by his whoring for the
climate change deniers,
there's a very persuasive
argument to be made...
that he's worse than Hitler.
(STUTTERS) Right, well...
And I'd appreciate it if
you'd stop working for him.
Okay, um, well... (STUTTERS)
so, I have moved up significantly,
and this might sound dumb,
but maybe I can kind of
work it from the inside,
- and that way...
- If you refuse,
I think it's well within my rights...
to remove your name from
amongst the beneficiaries
of my last will and testament.
Okay.
Because that's... that's
quite a pretty penny.
Around 250 mil.
And I'm sure Greenpeace
would be very much obliged.
No, de... definitely,
that is quite a pickle.
- EWAN: Mm.
- That is a tough one.
- (SLOT MACHINE CHIMING)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- Dude. (GROWLS PLAYFULLY)
- Hey, brother.
Oh, my God, you smell like cotton candy.
I almost want to lick
your neck. (LAUGHS)
Thanks for coming, man.
My dad'll be very pleased
when he sees, you know,
old friends and...
Hi, yes, sir. Yeah, I'll take
one of those golden beauties.
What's this?
Scottish. I'm thinking of getting in.
Scottish kicky-ball?
It looks like two eunuchs
trying to fuck a letterbox.
I'm liking the look of Hibs. Or Hearts.
- Yeah?
- Mm.
Hearts, that's my dad's team.
The only childhood relic he can stomach.
- Agent in Spain, big baller.
- Mm-hm.
I buy the club, he loans
me nine shit hot players.
- ROMAN: Mm-hm.
- We climb the ladder,
take the second Champion's League space,
UEFA goes full European super-league,
flip it, walk away.
I have no idea what
you're talking about,
but it sounds fucking slick, dude.
Slicker than cum on a dolphin's back.
You want in?
ROMAN: Hm. Maybe.
Uh... But can we talk
about what we talked about?
You know, a major injection,
or even taking us private.
Have you talked to your dad?
It's a conversation we can have.
Then we should totally have
that fucking conversation,
like two fucking auctioneers on coke.
I have total 360 latitude to
work on my father's behalf.
Oh, cool. Same with
me, with my dad, yeah.
Fuck, it's weird how
much we're the same.
(INHALES SHARPLY, GROWLS PLAYFULLY)
Attaboy.
Sock it in the net sack,
you crazy kick ball bastards.
- Buy them with me.
- Hmm?
Fifty-fifty.
Buy the... them? The...
Uh... Yeah, let me have a think.
I mean, I don't really see
a downside, other than...
zero knowledge or interest
in Scottish football,
but yeah, let me have
a little think. Hearts.
(JESSICA MOANS)
KENDALL: Are you just
looking at golf courses?
- (CHUCKLES)
- Like golf porn.
Am I allowed to take those
soaps in the bathroom?
Yeah. Fuck it, take it all.
- (KNOCKING ON DOOR)
- (JENNIFER SIGHS)
KENDALL: Yeah.
- CONNOR: Hi.
- KENDALL: Hey, Connor.
- Whatcha doing?
- Uh... We're just getting ready.
- CONNOR: Good.
- KENDALL: What time's... Uh...
What time's the thing?
I don't think the big
surprise is until eight.
- So...
- Willa asked me to check in,
'cause Jennifer is, like,
a key member of the cast.
Would it be possible
to send Jennifer back to be on stage?
Well, no, I'm afraid,
because Jennifer and
I are currently engaged
in one of the all-time great
psychosexual expeditions.
We're like the Lewis
and Clarke of fucking.
Come on, man. I'm begging you here.
I... I'm bleeding out.
I can't afford this.
I'm sorry, dude, but,
uh, that's showbiz.
- I am very unhappy with this outcome.
- KENDALL: I... I know.
I'm sorry.
(JENNIFER SCREAMS, LAUGHS)
Not wanting to put a dampener
on Rhea's celebrations
or anything, but it's
time we killed her dead.
Smash her skull in with a rock.
- Nice.
- KENDALL: Okay.
Way to ease us in, sis.
Will there be nibbles at this
event? I was expecting nibbles.
SHIV: What I'm thinking is
we just... We tell him direct.
We just tell him, all
of us, we won't have it.
- Should I maybe take the floor?
- SHIV: Okay.
Would Rhea really be the
worst thing in the world?
Or does a woman from outside
actually make sense right now?
(SCOFFS) Okay, right.
Well, she... she got to you.
- No. Just...
- (SHIV SCOFFS)
I'm fighting on two fronts
and I might have to
make a request to Dad
about a bridge situation,
- and she's been understanding.
- This is bullshit. Ken?
- Well...
- SHIV: Well?
Oh, come on.
Oh sh... You're backing
her too, rebounder?
No, I... I just...
- I just think that maybe...
- SHIV: You just...? You are.
... you've overplayed your hand.
Excuse me? How did she get to you?
Oh, you think you'll be given
another shot at some point,
ever? No.
- And, Roman, you? No.
- Ah, well, I mean...
No, she thinks you're a dipshit,
or maybe you're just too much
of a fucking dipshit to see that.
Fuck you. I know more about
this business than you.
- More than any of you, actually.
- Oh, Roman, no one gives a fuck
- about management training.
- Dad does. Gerri does.
It's corporate daycare.
(MIMICS IN CHILDISH
BABBLE, MAKES FART NOISE)
- (CONNOR LAUGHS)
- That's not a good retort!
- Don't fucking laugh at that.
- KENDALL: Shiv.
- Thanks for taking this seriously.
- ROMAN: I do.
It's just... It's transparent.
- Uh...
- KENDALL: You know, Rhea's who Dad wants.
Clearly. So...
- SHIV: (LAUGHING) But he's wrong.
- KENDALL: Yeah, but...
- In case you want it in writing.
- KENDALL: Maybe, you know,
you should just, like...
like, give it up.
Full disclosure, I'm
starting to like her.
(MOCKINGLY) Hmm. He likes her.
Yeah, this is why you don't
hatch a plan with Connor,
the first fucking pancake.
First pancake. Okay, thank you.
You're a brat. You know,
none of you have been through
what I've been through, so just...
(MOCKINGLY) Aw! My mommy
got sent to the booby hatch
- and now I'm sad.
- Fuck off.
I think you're being too
emotional about this whole thing.
- Oh, my fucking God.
- ROMAN: I think he's trying...
- Are you doing the emotional card on me?
- ... to mansplain things to you.
- Fuck's sake.
- I mean...
I mean, I was gonna mansplain it to you,
- but I think he did a very good job.
- (SHIV SCOFFS)
(INHALES SHARPLY)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
(CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING)
SHIV: Roman, Kendall and Connor.
Basically, it was a fucking disaster.
- TOM: Well, I'm sorry.
- (SIGHS) No, we just need to...
let him know, be very direct:
she tried to put her
hands down your pants.
No!
Seriously? That's not
a normal thing to ask?
SHIV: Not actually say that
she tried to... I don't know.
And I mean because also,
maybe, there is a world
in which Rhea...
makes more sense... for me
is the... is the truth. Maybe.
Excuse me? The woman who you barely know
makes more sense to you than your wife?
Oh, come on, it's complicated.
- (SHIV SCOFFS)
- Your dad is complicated.
You think if you kill Rhea,
he's just gonna give it
back to you automatically?
No.
Okay, well, Tom, I won't give up.
I won't.
He made me a fucking offer,
and I'm gonna redeem that coupon.
So, we got, uh, the Lord Provost,
the Chamber of Commerce,
Leader of the Council...
What? 20 to 30 faces?
- Is that right?
- I don't know.
Je suis pas ta secretaire.
Uh-huh.
Uh... Look, you stay
as long as you like,
I'm gonna bolt after the
soup, say I have calls.
I just wanna get the fuck out.
Okay.
♪ (TRADITIONAL SCOTTISH
FOLK MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
EWAN: Feting the king.
Tacitus comes to mind.
Yeah, yeah. Tacitus. Classic Tacitus.
He's made a wasteland
and calls it an empire.
God, Tacitus... (STUTTERS)
He just... just...
All killer, no filler with him.
Did he ever have a bad quote?
Have you tendered your resignation?
Just working that out
in the old noggin still.
CONNOR: Whoa.
Apparently...
we may be suffering from bad buzz.
Whatever good buzz we had
has been wiped out
by pervasive bad buzz.
GERRI: Okay, news. Huddle.
Okay, everyone. Here we go. Here we go.
♪ (MUSIC STOPS) ♪
Okay, everybody.
Um... Bright eyes, and
let's see those chompers.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
ALL: Surprise!
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
LOGAN: Jesus H. Christ!
♪ (MUSIC RESUMES) ♪
They're all in there!
I mean, I... I... I saw
Peter fucking Magillan.
Uh... Fucking Cyd.
Jeff Greenway. I mean, fuck me.
I... I thought it was
supposed to be a...
- You know, a steak and a chat.
- Rhea thought it would be nice.
Well...
Shall we?
Oh.
(CHEERING)
(LOGAN GRUMBLES)
(APPLAUSE)
Wow.
-(JENNIFER GASPS)
-KENDALL: I've never seen these.
- (PHONE CHIMES)
- Yeah, look at that. I think that's...
maybe the Denver Chronicle.
- (PHONE CHIMES)
- I interned there.
KENDALL: Everything okay?
Oh. (INHALES SHARPLY) Yeah.
It's... (CLEARS THROAT)
Word got around that I'm over here
and people from the
play are super-pissed.
Oh. Don't worry, don't worry.
We'll figure it out. Yeah?
Okay. (GROANS) Okay.
So, this was actually
a pretty tough situation
with the distribution,
- but my dad did this amazing...
- Has anyone ever told you
that you talk about
your dad, like... a lot?
(CHUCKLES) Okay. Uh...
No, I don't think they have.
(CHUCKLES) I wasn't trying to be nasty,
I was just pointing something out.
No, it's cool, he's...
he's just a major presence
in our lives.
Do you want to say hi?
- Okay. Yeah.
- Yeah? Yeah.
- I mean, he looks kind of busy.
- Let's go. Yeah, no, no, no.
- I want you to meet my dad.
- JENNIFER: Okay.
He's gonna love you.
I've got a proposition for you.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
So, we've got this opportunity
for you to become involved
financially in Willa's play,
which I don't know if
you've been hearing,
but the buzz is excellent.
- Hmm. Hmm.
- You know?
So, I'd really like to
talk to you about that,
- if I could. Just, you know...
- Uh...
Hey, Dad. This is Jennifer.
- JENNIFER: Hi. (CHUCKLES)
- Ah.
Pleasure to meet you.
It's nice to meet you, too.
Yeah, and congratulations,
too. This is so awesome.
- Thank you.
- JENNIFER: Yeah.
KENDALL: Jennifer's
really amazing, and, uh...
- (CHUCKLES) Thanks.
- LOGAN: Uh-huh.
- She's in theatre.
- Ah.
JENNIFER: Well, not really.
Well... (CHUCKLES) I
mean, you are. You are...
- You are.
- (GIGGLES) Shh.
Anyways, this is so awesome.
Yes, it is.
(CLOCKS TONGUE) I, uh...
I should really mingle, uh...
- So good to meet you.
- JENNIFER: Yeah.
Seen Kendall's latest?
Uh... Yeah.
- Mind like a balloon.
- (SHIV CHUCKLES)
SHIV: Uh-huh.
Hey, uh, you wanna... (INHALES SHARPLY)
You wanna call a truce for tonight?
LOGAN: Okay.
SHIV: I got you something.
Oh. Thank you.
LOGAN: Nice.
Oh, nice houses.
- Uh-huh. Yeah, these are...
- Lovely.
These are our houses, Dad.
- They're all ours.
- Really?
Yeah. Malibu.
- Uh-huh.
- You remember...
Huh. Quality work.
Don't like the past too much, huh?
I do. I do.
It's, uh... it's just
there's so much of it.
The future is real, but...
the past, well, it's...
Yeah. Um...
It's all made up.
It's, um... bad this time.
LOGAN: (SIGHS) She doesn't drink...
Uh... She's got my contacts
and everyone, everyone is here.
And I didn't know a thing.
Yeah.
- She's blue, you know?
- Uh-huh.
LOGAN: She's liberal.
Well, yeah, but so am I.
- Yeah, but you fucking get it.
- Kinda...
- You fucking get it. You know?
- (SHIV LAUGHS)
I mean, she told me she drank.
I shared a whisky with her.
- Mm-hm.
- Prick tease.
Oh, we don't use that anymore.
Oh, yeah. I know, I know.
All sorts of useful fucking
words have gone that way.
(SHIV SNORTS)
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
I'm worried.
- SHIV: Don't worry, Dad.
- Is it...
Have I got it right?
LOGAN: Huh?
'Cause...
You're smart. You are smart.
GERRI: I... 'Scuse
me, sorry to interrupt.
Just wanted to, um, ask you something
- about the procedures tonight.
- LOGAN: Oh, sure.
- GERRI: Question about cake.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. No, I, uh...
- I gotta go to the pisser.
- Okay. (CHUCKLES)
- Where is it?
- GERRI: Just... Oh, I think it's that way.
LOGAN: Hey.
(FAUCET RUNNING)
Uncle Logs.
Hey, I just, uh...
I just wanted to say "Happy Night".
Uh-huh.
I don't know, uh...
(TOWEL DISPENSER WHIRS)
I don't know. I just wanted to, uh...
(STUTTERS) It may be that I've
reached the end of the road
in terms of, uh... of... of like...
What?
My grandpa has made it clear
that if I want to secure my future,
then I need to sever my links.
Negotiate a bit of a "Grexit".
Did he now?
It has been a pleasure, um...
work... doing business with
you, and I've learned a lot.
And I hope that, um...
I hope that I brought
something to the table, too.
I like you, Greg.
Oh. O... Okay. Right.
I do. I like you.
What did he say?
He threatened to cut me off.
He won't do that.
He's too much of a fucking coward.
That's why his whole life
has amounted to nothing.
But you know, in the end,
it's up to you, kiddo. Hmm?
Yeah.
Uncle Fun...
or Grandpa Grumps.
So, I hereby convene the
meeting of the newly formed
"What the Fuck are We
Gonna Do" committee.
So we made the second threat
slash offer to Mr. Weissel
- and he said no.
- To what?
He said no to everything.
We offered 20 million
dollars. Didn't flinch.
No fear of the cost of legal action.
Zero appetite to settle.
We asked for a number. Any number.
- Apparently, this is no number.
- SHIV: There's no number?
And there's obviously something
going on under the water.
- We think he has a backer?
- Who?
Could be anyone who has
a grudge against Waystar.
Get a phone book. I mean,
it's a very long list.
It's all likely to come
out: the shadow logs,
- NDA, domino unraveling.
- Oh, mother!
It's spiraling. It's moving fast.
We hear the weasel. The weasel
is negotiating to go on TV
- and spill his guts. Yeah.
- Oh, fuck.
- GERRI: Uh-huh. It's gonna be huge.
- Fuck.
It's gonna blow wide open.
Sour any CEO announcement.
The new face is gonna
get ripped to shreds.
HUGO: Short term question is:
When... do we tell him?
Do we tell him tonight?
Anyone want to end the night
with a round of Boar on the Floor?
FRANK: Big picture, I mean... (SIGHS)
The weasel is an existential threat.
(INHALES) Okay.
We give him the night off.
Let him enjoy the night.
We'll tell him tomorrow.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
And if I had to tell
him you made the call,
would you still be happy with the call?
That's the call.
Uh... Good evening, everyone.
It's a pleasure to have you here tonight
to honor my dad's life and work.
(APPLAUSE)
So, when Rhea was planning
this, she asked me to help out
with, um... with a little
tribute to the certain...
flavor.
And after a lot of convincing, well...
- Here we are.
- ♪ (HIP HOP MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
Is he about to strip?
- KENDALL: Just remember I'm not a professional.
- Think he's going to masturbate
onstage to a photo of Dad.
KENDALL: My boy Squiggle
cooked up this beat for me.
Check it.
♪ Born on the North Bank
king of the East Side ♪
♪ Fifty years strong now
he's rollin' in a sick ride ♪
♪ Handmade suits raking in loot ♪
- ♪ Five star general y'all best salute, yo ♪
- ROMAN: Oh, no.
- No. Jesus, no. No.
- TABITHA: (LAUGHS) Oh, my God!
Ken. W.A.
(RAPPING CONTINUES)
I mean it's... it is burning my eyes,
but I cannot look away.
♪ L to the OG ♪
♪ Dude be the OG ♪
♪ A-N he playin' ♪
♪ Playin' like a pro, see ♪
♪ L to the OG ♪
♪ Dude be the OG ♪
♪ A-N he playin' ♪
♪ Playin' like a pro ♪
Make some noise!
- ♪ A1 ratings, 80K wine ♪
- (CROWD CHEERS)
♪ Never gonna stop, baby
fuck father time, bro ♪
♪ Don't get it twisted
I've been through hell ♪
♪ But since I stan Dad
I'm alive and well ♪
♪ Shaper of views creator of news ♪
♪ Father of many paid all his dues ♪
♪ So don't try to run
your mouth at the king ♪
♪ Just pucker up, bitch
and go kiss the ring ♪
♪ L to the OG ♪
♪ Dude be the OG ♪
♪ A-N he playin' ♪
- Make some noise!
- (CROWD CHEERS)
♪ When I say L, you say OG ♪
♪ L to the... ♪
- ♪ L to the... ♪
- CROWD: ♪ OG ♪
- You need to stop this.
- ♪ L to the... ♪
- ♪ OG ♪
♪ L to the... ♪
♪ L to the motherfucking OG ♪
- I think this might be the end of the company.
- (CHEERING)
We might get sucked into a
black hole of embarrassment
that we never get out of.
Dundee in the motherfucking house.
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
If I can get your attention.
Some appreciations of the
man, the legend, Logan Roy.
(APPLAUSE)
KENDALL: (ON FILM) Hey,
Dad. Hey, everybody.
Um...
Yeah, you all know that
I've had my ups and downs...
you could say.
And, um...
What you might not know is
that my dad has been the one
who's been to meet me
at my lowest moments...
Hey, uh, sorry to interrupt.
You remember Eduard?
Just wanna say congrats on
a lifetime of kicking ass.
Thanks. I'm not dead yet.
Um... Also, I got you a present.
We actually got you a present.
We bought the Hearts.
WOMAN: (ON FILM) Logan,
happy anniversary...
- The Hearts?
- Mm-hm!
- Hearts Football Club?
- Why?
- Why... Because it's the Hearts.
It's your team.
- I'm Hibs.
- You're Hibs?
- Really?
- LOGAN: Uh-huh.
Are you sure?
I thought you were Hearts.
I'm pretty sure, Dad.
You know, maybe you're right.
How would I know what team I
supported all my fucking life?
I mean, maybe I support Kilmarnock.
Or Fucklechester Rangers?
I mean, how can I fucking
possibly fucking know?
If it's any consolation,
I'm horrible at gift buying.
Yeah. Always get the wrong thing.
Oh, hey, it's me. Watch it.
ROMAN: (ON FILM) What can I say?
Congrats on a thousand years...
- Hey.
- LOGAN: Hey, Shiv.
Listen, I... I really... I really am...
wondering about this. Rhea.
Dad. Listen. You gotta do
what you think is right.
Yeah? That's all there is.
And she's the one.
For now, she's the one.
SHIV (ON FILM): Hey, Dad. Congrats!
Uh... (SCOFFS)
Look, I know how you
hate all this bullshit,
so I'll just say... "Fuck you, Dad",
and I wish we were having
wine instead of being here
with all these people
who are scared of you.
(CHUCKLES)
Just try your gut. Yeah?
You can't give it to me
or anyone else because of sentiment.
You know that.
Thank you, darling.
Thank you.
Yeah.
ASSISTANT: 30 seconds to VT, Mr. Roy.
You all right?
- Was it... Was it all too much?
- (APPLAUSE)
I'm not crazy about surprises.
LOGAN: Uh...
I wasn't expecting so
many friendly faces.
I mean, you got me, you bastards.
- You know, you really got me.
- (LAUGHING)
Uh...
But seriously, no. I'm touched.
Um...
Some people say that
I'm wedded to my work.
Just ask any of my wives.
(SCATTERED CHUCKLING)
But I'm amazed at what
Waystar has achieved
over the last 50 years.
And I'm proud of my family,
who have helped me get here.
And it seems to me that now,
after 50 years at the helm...
now might be a smart
time to think about...
who will help me write the next chapter.
I'm gonna announce
tonight, in due course,
I shall be appointing...
Rhea Jarrell...
as my chief executive officer.
- (APPLAUSE)
- LOGAN: Statement to follow.
♪ (MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
Hey! That was pretty intense.
(SIGHS)
Uh...
Yeah.
You, um... (CHUCKLES)
You said... You said "awesome" a lot.
(CHUCKLES) What?
(CHUCKLES) You said "awesome" a lot
when you were talking to my dad.
Did I? (CHUCKLES) Okay.
I didn't notice that.
It's fine. It was just... It was funny.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
You're freezing. Let me...
Let me get your coat.
- I'll be right back.
- Okay.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hey, can we get Jennifer on
the first flight outta here?
Sure thing. Everything okay?
Uh... Yeah. Good.
Maybe... Hey. Hey, Tony.
Maybe, um... let her know
I might be tied up. Okay.
Excuse me.
- Nice night, eh?
- Mm-hm.
You okay?
You told me nothing about
you stepping aside. Why?
I apologize.
You broke something here.
I didn't like it...
when you told me that I
should sell my company.
You hear what you wanna hear,
then you punish me for
something I didn't say.
I may have made some misjudgments.
You're careless.
- You've been careless of me.
- Marcia.
I'm bored. You are boring me.
Excuse me, it's time for
the plaque now, Mr. Roy.
- I'm going.
- LOGAN: Marcia.
Don't be fucking stupid. It's a plaque.
(WHISPERS) Oh, God forbid, I
will miss the plaque. Right?
Your shiny little gravestone.
Guess you'll have to
face your reckoning alone.
Mother would have hated all this.
And that trash you call news.
Now, we last saw her
when you were five...
and I was four...
but you know what kind of journalism
she would've approved of?
I know she never would've
approved of what you've become.
What? Your meal ticket?
I'm just surprised
you're still standing.
Any other man would've
died from the shame.
- Uh-huh.
- It's hard to know
which is more toxic:
your news outlets or
your cruise division.
All those years blaming
yourself for Rose.
- I'm not interested.
- That really wasn't your fault.
This, though...
This is your fault.
This empire of shit.
Time to pay up.
MC: Ladies and gentlemen,
it is that time.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(APPLAUSE)
MC: The Helen Elspeth Roy College!
♪ (MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
WOMAN: Sexual exploitation,
violence, hidden by
cover-ups and corruption
inside Waystar.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
Gregory Hirsch.
Is that someone known
to you, Mr. Wambsgams?
Uh, no, no, sorry.
No, Tom?
As the next CEO, it might
be wise to keep clean.
That scares me.
Any chance you guys have the
muscle to take us private?
Outside! I can't have this now!
Ten bad minutes on camera in D.C....
That could be it, the end.
♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
Mr. Roy, a pleasure to welcome you home.
Oh, I don't recall people
shedding a tear when I left.
JESSE ARMSTRONG: It's a pretty
touching episode to make
because Brian Cox, the actor,
comes from Dundee in Scotland.
He was the guy driving around
places he knew from his youth
as he plays Logan, being
a guy driving around
places that he knows from his youth, so,
it was very affecting to see that.
This place, you look at the old pictures
and they all want you to think it's all
so fucking simple, but it wasn't.
What they say, you know?
ARMSTRONG: In the writer's
room, we always knew there was
an element of tragedy in his early life.
There it is. What am I supposed to do?
I think maybe a photo.
They've said you can go in.
No, thank you. Let's go.
Ahh, memories.
- Marcia, you look lovely.
- Oh, thank you.
Uh, so... Something
I wanted to ask you...
ARMSTRONG: Marcia, she
doesn't come from the same
cultural background as
the rest of the characters,
and so her rhythms
are slightly different.
Are you regularly tested for
sexually transmitted diseases?
Excuse me? (CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
He and I still sleep together,
so I would be more relaxed
to know that you are clean.
And I think she shocks people
and puts them on their heels,
so it was interesting
seeing her do that to Rhea.
(STAMMERS) This isn't
appropriate talk...
When I lose...
the other one will
generally lose an eye or so.
CROWD: Surprise!
Rhea organizes what we
call the Logan-athon.
She thinks it will be nice.
LOGAN ROY: Jesus H. Christ.
ARMSTRONG: I don't know whether
she's quite judged, exactly,
things that Logan prizes in life,
which are generally about going forward,
not huge on the past.
It's a pleasure to have
you here tonight to honor
my dad's life and work.
Rhea asked me to help out
with a little tribute to the
certain, uh, flava.
ARMSTRONG: The idea of Kendall rapping
was, I remember, I was thinking,
if you heard a billionaire's
son had done that,
it would be like, yeah,
sounds like the sort of
toe-curling thing you
might see on Instagram.
(RAPPING) ♪ L to the
O-G dude be the OG ♪
♪ A-N, he playin' ♪
ARMSTRONG: It was nice, and
we had that whole V and A
in Dundee that was full
of background people
and people just responded naturally.
I think it's pretty embarrassing.
It's also kind of good.