- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
We're going for PGM.
We leverage up and eat Pierce,
we're too big for Sandy
and Stewey to come for.
We all like this?
Contact with the family did
have one heavyweight they liked.
Frank.
It's not been the same without you.
It's been better.
Carolina has bad news
about the biography.
The writer, anyone who speaks to her,
they're dead to me.
You're pals with Naomi Pierce, right?
You want to use Naomi to broker a deal?
Bingo.
The Pierce family got word
that you were on maneuvers.
We need to back right off.
Someone spiked Pierce.
Which one of you boars did it?
Boar on the floor.
- What are you hiding?
- What are you...
It was Roman.
He took a call from Naomi Pierce.
Roman, you're a moron.
Who backs me on Pierce?!
They're all against it.
We are going after it.
How do I get him to take me seriously?
Do the management training program.
Ground floor.
Pierce's CEO, Rhea
Jarrell, she can help us.
Okay, it's time to bring you in.
Hey, Rhea.
Hey, it's Kendall Roy again.
Uh, I hope this isn't getting weird.
Um... Yeah, I just, uh,
wanted to check in and, uh...
Frank gave me the impression
it was cool to make contact.
Just hoping we can, uh... Yeah,
we can make this happen today.
Would just be good to connect.
Okay. Thanks.
So?
- What?
- First day in.
- Uh, it's more of a fact finder.
- Sure, but it's exciting, no?
It's like you and your
dad have finally admitted
how much you're into
each other, you know.
And now you can... You know, not this,
but now you can bang.
Uh-huh.
Uh... so what's the current
thinking on Ravenhead?
Ravenhead, uh, stick with
him. Young talent, nice guy.
Your dad likes him, and, uh,
he's one of our most popular anchors.
Yeah, sure, but is he a fascist?
Well, that's a very loaded word.
You've seen the video, Tom.
He's right there with the fascists.
It was a long time ago.
He was interested in politics,
he gets invited to a conference,
he's excited, he has no idea who he's...
who he's sitting on a panel with,
It's all perfectly plausible.
Oh, yeah, it's
plausible, but is it true?
Shiv, come on. Who wasn't
a bit salty when they were 21?
He's grown up now. He
lives in Connecticut.
He's crazy about the Knicks,
he's... he's a lovely guy.
And... and his demo skews younger.
The fuck is this?
Ravenhead fanboys.
Ugh. Morning, assholes.
Hey, those are our assholes.
Great. Well, technically,
they're your assholes.
Say it loud, say it clear,
Ravenhead is welcome here!
Say it loud, say it clear...
Okay. Now who are these assholes?
This could get ugly.
Can you imagine if someone
actually cleaned up here, Tom?
With a cleansing fucking zeal?
Uh-huh. Like Mary
Poppins with a hard on?
No, like me. Or you.
This is it. Wish me luck.
All right. I'm exiting
Earth's atmosphere.
The prince is departing the palace.
See you in six weeks.
If I don't come back, send goons.
They may sacrifice me to their gods.
Welcome to management training.
- Oh...
- Itinerary.
Oh, thanks. Okay.
Welcome, everyone.
Congratulations to all of you
for being selected to be here.
This is very exciting. You all excited?
Yeah. All right.
After this short video,
we'll get you out
for a taste of the park in costume.
Okay.
Waystar Royco is a family.
a family that spans four continents,
fifty countries, three divisions:
entertainment, news, and resorts.
Working together to provide
a net that can hold the world,
or catapult it forward
to the next adventure.
Joining Waystar Royco,
you're joining one of the most dynamic
news and entertainment
companies in the world.
Feel it.
Waystar diversity and harassment policy.
Waystar Royco has worked
hard to develop a tolerant
and respectful workplace.
The company is strongly committed
to making employment decisions
based on valid requirements,
and without regards to
race, color, religion
or religious creed,
age, national origin,
ancestry, gender, gender identity,
gender expression...
What the fuck happened with the video?
What do you mean?
I've been cut. It's
me and some satellites
for, like, three seconds.
I'll find out.
It's not a big deal, Gerri.
I don't care how many minutes I get,
it's just the message it sends.
Sure thing. I get it.
So, uh, how is it going?
Oh, amazing.
I'm stripping back to basics.
This is my White Album.
Is it very horrible in America?
Oh, yes. It's glorious, yeah.
No amount of antibacterial gel
is gonna be able to
wipe the America off me.
This is good for you, Rome.
I know. I'm gonna grow up
and become a real little boy,
and learn the price of an egg,
and do phone sex with my
girlfriend like a normo.
You'll be fine.
Just be brave, okay?
Yes, Mommy.
Welcome to the family.
Yeah. Finally in.
So, what's on the slab?
Proxy battle tactical shit.
Good to have your PR thoughts.
- Yeah.
- Distributors.
Check in on Ravenhead. Mo's funeral.
Uh-huh.
So, where should I
base myself? In there?
Not there. That's Kendall.
He has his office,
but on the proxy battle, we keep close.
Mm-hmm. Makes sense.
We'll find you somewhere.
Something nearby.
Yeah. Whatever. I'll float.
So, every day begins with champagne?
Let's, uh... get hammered
and buy a mining company in Tanzania.
Why not?
Hey, Dad.
It's time.
- Hey, Shiv.
- Hey.
With food, this yellow one.
I thought Joan was on his medication.
Joan missed a dose.
So, just till we have a
system that we can rely on...
Your sister's just in for the day.
Oh, yeah?
Okay. Whatever.
- Just to observe.
- Cool.
Just to observe what?
It's not a big deal, Ken.
No, sure. Good point.
Good, uh, observation.
Lucy, can you find Shiv somewhere?
I'm gonna prep with Ken.
Twenty minutes.
- You good?
- Yeah.
Hey, hey! Dirk Turkey!
Can we get a photo?
Of course!
- Hey, picture time.
- Oh, excuse me.
Hey, um, can you take a photo for us?
Thank you so much.
All right, here we go.
- Right.
- Hello!
So I'm guessing you
two aren't fucking much?
- Excuse me?
- You need to get home
and figure this shit out.
This is a sad state
of affairs, my friend.
This woman needs satisfaction
that you are clearly not providing.
Thanks for coming. Enjoy the park.
What was that?
I said "gobbledy go fuck yourself!"
So, I'm just curious, Greg.
What does it mean
being executive assistant to Tom?
Um, well, I... I perform
a variety of target-oriented tasks,
and keep close to the deal flow,
- and...
- Sort of, kind of like a...
like a farm hand? Clip his coat?
Uh, do you have to milk him?
Uh, no. I just, uh, keep my head down,
and keep the lattes flowing, you know?
You're a smart cookie, you know?
- Mm-hmm.
- We should talk.
Greg! When you're done flirting,
can you latte me, please?
Oh, ho! Farewell, lords
and masters of the board.
Time for the real meeting.
Hey hey! Who's the hot intern?
I'm not here. I'm just observing.
_
She's coming. Rhea. We got her.
Excellent.
- It's real?
- As I understand it.
Uh, family doesn't
know she's coming, so...
Right? I mean, why lie to
the old lady, unless, uh...
you're down to fuck?
Now, this is, uh, us three.
- We're the group on this
- Yeah. The family trusts her.
You get her on board, that's huge.
She could be our Coriolanus.
He switched sides.
You know, why don't you
take your library card and...
fuck off?
So...
What's first?
Ravenhead.
I'm getting carpet bombed on this.
FCC, ADL.
Pierce News is all over it,
and Antifa has turned up.
Can we not get a water
cannon down there?
You know, give 'em a fucking shower,
fucking animals.
The police have it
under control, I believe.
Well, yeah, but I don't think
it's smart to sugar-coat it.
To me, "ATN under siege".
- That's our line.
- Agreed. Endorsed.
And, uh, I've managed
to talk the advertisers
down off the ledge,
so I think we just
weather the storm, right?
Well, the problem is we've
been asked to comment,
because, um, apparently Mark...
Records show that he got
married at the Eagle's Nest,
Hitler's retreat in Bavaria.
A chapel below.
Oh, God.
Uh, ignore that.
- She's not here.
- His agent assures me
that it was a coincidence,
they were on vacation
in the area.
Yeah, well, fuckin' big coincidence.
Uh...
Is that curtains?
I think he's toast.
Right? We just toss him.
Hey. Come on. No coaching
from the sidelines.
Uh, no. I'm not here.
Oh, right. I forgot. You're not here.
Well, what do you say, Ken?
Hey. Enough. Cyd?
We don't wanna fire
him. He's a big draw.
And if we cave to this, then who's next?
Tom, check him out,
turn his guts inside out.
Uh, but nah. We back
talent. Ravenhead stays.
Connor, you ready?
You okay, honey? I know
how you are about death.
Okay, not so sad.
This is a big opportunity for me, baby.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Campaign financing.
Mo knew a lot of
high-net-worth individuals.
I'm gonna work the room,
meet some wallets.
The whole church is gonna
be stuffed with weeping ATMs.
Right. So, Marcia called.
Marcia? She called you?
Yeah. She wanted me
to talk to the widow,
see what Mo told the biographer?
No, this is good!
They're involving you in their
disgusting little stratagems.
- Right.
- It means they like you.
Come on. Let's get ready to
shed a tear at Mo's funeral,
AKA the gold rush.
I'm getting a donor boner
just thinking about it.
That's cute.
Yo! Hey.
Oh...
Hey, Greg. What's going on?
Jonah, say hi.
- Hey, Greg.
- Hey, Jonah.
Hey, I'm thinking of taking
things to the next level.
- Uh-huh?
- Footstool fiesta.
We had a bet, Jonah lost.
Be his turn to do it to me one day.
Come on!
Um...
- Just, uh...
- Go ahead.
Yeah. Let... Let me
know if I'm too heavy.
Yep. Will do.
So, uh, Herr Ravenhead. Do
you have anything for me,
ahead of my meet?
Um... Honestly, I've been,
uh, been asking around,
and not much. Uh,
I heard he named his dog
after Hitler's dog, maybe.
Blondi.
That's not good.
But, you know, Logan
likes and America likes,
and "Blondi" is pretty common.
No, but I mean, fascist meeting,
Nazi wedding, Hitler dog...
Oh, dude. If it's true, he's gone.
I mean, Nazis, terrible, right?
Nazis?
- Yeah.
Yeah, they're... they're the worst.
Yeah, sure. We all hate
Nazis. And we all hate Cyd.
Right, Jonah?
If we look at the aggregate
of all employment opportunities
available on Earth right now,
this is top one, two percent.
We are basically in heaven.
Well, aren't you positive.
They'll beat that out of you.
What's your story, Hunky Dory?
Me? I'm an enigma.
You can't pigeon-hole me.
I'm there, then I'm gone.
I'm intellectually promiscuous,
but culturally conservative,
I work hard, but I do not
play hard. I play easy.
- Why would you play hard?
- Good question.
And what is it you're doing right now?
I'm lurking. Like a dormant virus.
Biding my time in the
Fort Meyers resort,
but I'm being stymied
by a variety of enemies
who are envious of my talents.
- Obviously.
- Brian.
Uh, yeah. Ron. Ron... Rockstone.
Sure, man. Very solid name.
In terms of proxy statements,
I'm not sure how much you need to see.
Uh, yeah. Maybe just show me everything.
Yeah, uh, because, uh,
that's a lot of material.
I can process pretty quick.
And after this perhaps
we sit down with my dad,
and go through PR strategy?
Oh. He's unavailable this afternoon.
Because what? Monkey
gland butt injection?
Yeah. Something like that!
Getting his hair blown out.
Yeah, his afternoon is greyed-out.
And then there's Mo's funeral.
Yeah...
Does Karolina know?
- Has Colin done his thing?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
- Thank you, Jess.
- Okay.
- What was that?
- Nothing.
Uh-huh. Sure.
Well, Jess, so Kendall.
And Karolina...
so public-facing. But Colin, too?
Grubby.
And Dad's in a secret meeting,
and I'm in here with a coloring book.
What's goin' on, Gerri?
Maybe you should talk to your dad.
Oh, come on. It's me. What's happening?
It's Kendall.
What, is he huffing Sharpies again?
Shoplifting.
He's stealing? Stealing what?
Candy and vape fluid, I believe.
He's stealing vape fluid?
What? He could buy the entire industry.
Well, is someone talking
to him? Is he suspended?
Hmm. We're cleaning it up
without getting him involved.
Oh, good. That'll teach him a lesson.
I'm sorry, what the fuck?
How many lives does this guy have?
Logan wants to keep it down low.
- Hey.
Just, uh, wanted to check
in and see how you're doing.
Good. Interesting. Yeah.
Yeah, great. So, uh, what's goin' on?
How are you?
What's your next move?
Are you thinking media?
Like, here, or somewhere else?
Division?
Yeah, you know, I don't know, but, uh...
- I... Do I have to tell you?
- No, sure.
Hey, listen.
- I know you lost your job.
- I walked out.
Okay, whatever. It's all good.
I just, uh... Yeah, I don't know. I...
- It's good to see you.
- Cool.
Maybe I should come in more often.
Ken? Your thing.
- She's en route.
- Okay.
- What's that?
- Ah, it's nothing.
Shiv, it's... it's, uh,
it's not a thing. Okay?
I just can't say.
That's fine, Ken. Do your secret shit.
You seem to be mistaking me
for someone you're in competition with.
Thanks.
Well, that was exciting.
Smuggled in like
Cleopatra in the carpet.
Yeah. Sorry for the cloak and dagger.
Rhea Jarrell.
And you must be Oedipus Roy?
- Uh...
- I'm teasing.
- Right.
- Are we this way?
Yeah, over here.
Sorry about the commotion outside.
Rhea Jarell, Logan Roy.
Dad, Rhea Jarrell.
It's lovely to have you.
Please, have a seat.
Now, can I get you something to drink?
Oh, just some water, thanks.
- Quite a view.
- Mm.
Lady Liberty.
So, the agenda of the meeting
is just to sort of, you know,
check in on how we can
all better work together
to protect journalists
in hostile environments,
- and any other areas...
- Uh, yeah, yeah,
thank you for the cover story
but we don't need to
bother with all that.
We know you're interested
in an acquisition again,
and, uh, I have a message.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
The message would be, on
behalf of the Pierce family,
and the media organization
that it's privately owned
for 150 years,
the message would be a
typically balanced, nuanced,
and objective "fuck off".
Very nuanced.
And is that the view
of the whole family?
They're united in that?
Well, I don't involve myself
in the palace intrigue,
but overall, the family
knows what you're after,
and they're not interested.
And what am I after?
You're playing your
favorite tune again, no?
Only this time, I take
it some genius banker
has convinced you that the
only way to keep the jackals out
is to leverage yourself until
you're too big to take down.
Well, I can assure you that
is not a fair characterization
- of what we're doing here.
- Look.
What do they want?
- The Pierces? In general?
- Mm-hmm.
- Who knows?
- So there is a price?
All I can say is that at this point, uh,
the position is they're not interested.
And you? What do you think?
I think they're amazing custodians.
So you don't have a position
on who your owner is,
because that would
presumably affect things,
- if you weighed in?
- I'm a chief executive.
I take my orders from the
board. I'm a mere tool.
- Uh-huh.
Anyway, I hope this hasn't
been too disappointing.
It's been fun.
You know, I want Pierce.
But it only works for me fast.
- Very fast.
- Mm-hmm.
So, please, stay. Have lunch.
Oh, uh... My tummy is delicate.
We really only eat
Pulitzer over at Pierce.
You eat.
I'll, uh...
stay for five and skulk
out the way I skulked in.
Okay, everyone, now
that you've found a partner,
for this next exercise,
I'd like you all to
come up with some ideas
for new rides or attractions.
And then, uh, work it up into a pitch,
and we're gonna present
to the group, okay?
What is this, fucking school?
We're pitching now?
What if we fuck it? What if
I can't think of anything?
I don't have anything prepared.
Did you know about this?
This is cool. Sounds
like a great exercise.
You have no fucking understanding
of how this works, do you?
Like, this, right here?
This is a rank and yank.
It's fucking up or out.
This is a death march
through a fucking minefield.
Okay, well, come on.
What do people like?
What do everyday people like?
Um, do... Everyday? How
the fuck should I know
what everyday people like?
I like booking out a
suite at the Chateau,
and snorting purified sertraline
off women that don't know
they're prostitutes yet.
Interesting hobby, Ron Rockstone.
Well, what do the normos
like? What do you like?
- Me?
- Yeah.
Okay, uh,
I enjoy spending time with
my nephews, Cooper and Clark.
I hike. I have several
high-end racing drones.
Oh, my God, stop.
No offense, but wow.
How about terror? Like, actual terror.
Like a VR experience, but like,
"I'm actually gonna
fucking die." Like war.
Like, we put you in one
of those landing crafts,
and you're about to hit the beach...
- Mm-hmm. Yeah.
- Normandy, you know what I'm saying?
No one's ever gone bust overestimating
the American public's
interest in violence.
Fuck yeah.
- Write this shit up.
- All right. Yeah.
Hey, Mark. Great to see you. Come on in.
I caught the show this morning.
Oh, great. Thanks.
Uh, where's Cyd?
She's out on a thing, but she's...
she thought it would be
great for us to check in,
and I'm... I'm a big fan.
Thank you. Thanks.
Uh, so Karyn tells me, uh,
you want the full colonoscopy,
- huh?
- Oh, dude. No, no.
We both know, I think,
how dumb these things are.
You know how it is.
It's just due diligence
with all the turbulence,
and, can I just...
just need to check a few boxes.
Sure, sure. Thank you
for the show of faith.
No, no. No... No problem. Okay, right.
Okay, so this is embarrassing,
but, um, just for the record,
and just so we have it, um...
You are not, and have never been
a member of the Nazi Party of
the United States, have you?
Come on, Tom. You serious?
Nope.
Thank you. Sorry to have to even ask.
Uh, bu-bu-bu-bu-bah...
And... Oh, yes, the Hitler dog thing?
- Okay, the dog thing's bullshit.
- Great. Great. I thought so.
Different spelling.
- Okay. Different spelling?
- Yeah.
Okay. Uh, and this
other one that came up,
just to fend this off, have
you ever read Mein Kampf?
Um... Yeah, couple of times, I guess.
Couple times?
Are there Easter eggs in there
you didn't get the first time?
Look, I'm... I'm just...
I'm interested in that
period of history, Tom. Okay?
- I skimmed it.
- Skimmed. Yeah. Thank you.
And, um... And what, specifically,
do you find interesting
about that period of history?
The scale. The tragedy.
Hell yeah. Yeah. Which
tragedy, specifically?
Europe decimated.
Seven million Germans,
twenty million Russians,
five million Poles.
Yeah. Just... Just checking
the till here, Mark,
and it seems you're short a few million.
- What was that?
- The fuck was that?
- Shooter. Shooter!
- What? What did he say?
- What did he say?
- Shooter.
Sir? Please... Please
follow me. Yeah. Come on.
- Do we have a safe room?
- We have a secure location.
Excuse me. Excuse me. Excuse me.
Excuse me. Executives coming through!
Gangway!
Apologies. There seems to
be a fire alarm sounding.
We'll find out the cause of
that and be right back with you,
after the break.
Please follow me. Everybody, please...
- please follow me.
- What's going on?
We have to evacuate.
Oh, God... Oh, my God.
What... What the fuck?
There was a gunshot
from somewhere down the hall.
Shooter in the building.
We think they got in.
- Holy shit!
- Where are the others?
Where's Logan and Shiv?
- Are we still on the air?
- I dunno.
This is them, right?
Antifa? Or a maniac?
Are they trying to come get us?
Maybe she's gone outside.
Maybe we should try to get outside.
- No, we should try...
- This is...
This is the safe room, okay?
This is the panic room.
- What? How is it safe?
- We're safe here.
- Calm down!
- It's just a room!
What is this? What's happening?
We'll get on that, sir.
- We just wanna get you safe.
- Where's Kendall? Is he safe?
We'll find them.
Open the door, please.
Thank you.
Shiv! Shiv, thank God! Thank God!
- Are you okay?
- Tom, what's going on?
I'm not sure. I'm hearing
crazies or maybe Antifa.
We think they were coming for me.
Coming for you?
Yeah, maybe. You know,
head of ATN. Decapitate.
Wait, what? Who said that?
Okay, well, where are you now?
Uh, I'm in the panic room with Greg.
Okay, great. I'm coming there now.
Okay, hurry. Be safe. See you soon.
Are you armed?
I'm not allowed to disclose
that information, sir.
Wait. If... If he's the target
maybe he should get his own room.
Thank you.
Hey.
- How you' doing?
- Hi. How you doing?
- You want anything?
- Uh...
- You want some water?
- Where's Kendall?
- Is he safe?
- Uh, yeah, I don't know.
What is this, Siobhan?
- Uh, Antifa maybe. They think.
- Pieces of shit.
Where's Tom?
So what are you hearing? Is it all over?
Things seem to have
calmed down, but honestly,
- I can't get a read, sir.
- Okay.
- Any updates?
- Hey, Shiv.
Tom, where are you?
- I'm with Dad.
- What? Where?
I... I'm in the fucking panic room!
There's two panic rooms?
I think... I'm in the wrong...
I'm in the wrong panic room.
Well, just, uh... Just
stay where you are. It's...
Is there more shooting?
Uh, no. No. It's all quiet here.
What a... How about you?
No. Good. Was there really a shooter?
I don't... I don't... Who else
is in there with you, Shiv?
- Is Cyd in there?
- No.
It's, uh, just me and...
Hey, uh, Tom, I should go.
Stay safe. I love you. Bye.
What the fuck? We got the shit room!
That makes total sense
because this safe room
doesn't feel that safe. Okay?
I mean, is that airtight?
Or... And is that bulletproof?
Are these windows bulletproof?
I mean, they could
waft gas in here. Right?
I don't think this
speculation is very helpful.
I mean, these are the
things you think about
when you're designing a panic room!
So, I'm just saying.
And a person can fit through there.
A person can definitely
fit through that window.
A small person. An attack child.
Okay, I need you to get
me to the other safe room,
- the real one, right away.
- Sir...
- Have you taken your pills?
- What?
- Does Kendall have your meds?
- I... I don't know.
You want something?
How's your blood sugar?
- You want some beef jerky?
- Yeah, maybe. Maybe.
- Oh. Hey. Are you okay?
- I was on my way out,
and, I have to say, this seems
like a very drastic way
of keeping me on the premises.
Here, come, sit. Are we on air yet?
Do you know who was hurt?
Waiting on updates.
Any more shots?
Rhea Jarrell. Hi.
Siobhan. How are you?
Uh, yeah. As good as I can be.
We're up. We're up.
... on the 15th floor, I heard the alarm
and was told to evacuate immediately.
We were rushed down
14 flights of stairs.
I heard one staffer who was
obviously very distressed
saying she heard a single gunshot,
and someone shouting, "Shooter!"
Everyone's okay, though?
Everyone's fine, but apparently
they're not gonna make the funeral.
I guess we can't leave too, right?
Didn't think so.
- Hi. Thank you for coming.
- Yeah.
I'm so sorry that Dad
didn't get to see him
- before he went.
- Yeah, he was asking for Logan.
I'm so sorry for your loss, Maria.
You know, I never met Mo,
but I heard that he
was just a great guy.
- Um, Mo?
- Your husband?
We're so sorry.
His name's not Mo.
- What? You call him Mo.
- His name's Lester.
Okay, so why does everyone call him Mo?
- His real name is Lester.
- It was...
I guess I haven't thought
about it for a while,
but it was kind of a joke.
- Like what?
- Mo-Lester.
I guess it wasn't a very nice joke.
- And was he one?
- Oh, God, no.
Just, you know...
Old Mr. Fiddlesticks, Uncle Meathands.
Right.
Dad wouldn't let us
in the pool with him.
But, you know, the guys
of that generation...
It was a different time.
Okay.
Let's get a donor on
the end of this boner.
I feel a PAC attack coming on.
It's like the old tunnel
of love, but much hipper.
- And you travel through it in...
- Bullshit.
- ... canoes shaped like vaginas.
- Our idea shits on their idea.
Thank you.
Don't fucking clap.
Okay. Who's next?
Oh, fuck. Okay. All right.
Don't fuck this up.
Don't screw it up.
Uh, thank you, everyone.
- So what we tried to do is...
- Uh, Mr. Roy?
...create an adult-focused attraction.
- Okay, so it's called...
- Mr. Roy, um,
just in case you get a
news alert on your phone,
there has been an incident at ATN.
- My dad okay?
- It's been suggested
it could be a concerted
attack against the family.
Do you want us to take you
to a more secure location?
Yeah, of course I want that.
Get me the fuck out of here.
This way.
There's a lot of confusion.
We have reporters currently
locked outside of the building.
I'm talking from
inside the control room.
This is not good, Greg.
They're just trying to
make me look like a coward.
Hiding in the fucking closet
while she's out there
breakdancing through gunfire.
You ran pretty quick.
You ran pretty fucking quick, too.
I was just behind you.
Everybody was running.
Lives here are at risk.
But we at ATN will not be cowed.
We're determined to fulfil...
Oh. Nobody hurt, it seems. One person.
Look, off the record, I
think we're in the clear.
We just need to hang out
for a little while longer.
- Wait for confirmation.
- Okay.
Oh, fuck.
Shut up.
Tom? Do you think, uh...
Do you think right now
might be a good time for a little chat?
Yeah? What, Greg?
Um, I've just been thinking
a lot recently, and, uh,
you know, uh... Yeah,
I don't know. Um...
I'm in the shadow of a giant here.
AKA you.
And, um, you know, like, do I wanna
maybe catch some sunlight
if I'm gonna grow?
Like, would it be okay for me
to maybe take... take a chance,
and go to another department?
What? I'm... I'm digging in here.
Yeah, you are. And I'm
just wondering, like,
would it be maybe
interesting for both of us
if I go work with somebody
else for a little bit?
Sorry.
Are you... Are you attempting
to break up with me, Greg?
It's... It's just...
Dude, ATN, human furniture, like...
Verbal assaults, physical humiliations,
Nazi stuff, shooters...
I just don't love it like I... I just...
I don't really love it,
and I wanna go explore.
Uh-huh.
And then I... And I can come back.
You know?
It could be like... like a
business open relationship.
This is not a good...
feeling, Greg, that you're
making me have, you know?
Can you stop crunching?
Sure. Yeah. I'm sorry.
Yeah, I'm feeling...
What?
I just... I feel a
little bit... You know?
I know, I know. It's just an idea.
Fuck.
- Fuck.
- Yeah.
Fuck.
Okay, Tom? Hey, hey, Tom. Tom.
- We're good. We're good.
- We're good?
We're good?
It doesn't feel fucking good, Greg!
Let's just... Can we...
I will not let you do this to me!
I will not let go of what is mine!
What... What... What...
What am I doing? Ow!
Stop pelting me!
- Fuck! Fuck!
- I was... Stop... Stop! Security!
- Guys!
- No, you back off! You back off!
This is executive level business!
- Okay? No!
- Stop, Tom! We're friends!
You're one of my best friends!
Are you okay, son? Where were you?
Yeah. I'm fine, Dad. I was fine.
It looks like there was only one.
An employee. ATN segment producer.
- What, he went postal?
- It was a suicide.
He shot himself at his desk.
Colin, I need a little more time...
Hey. You okay?
Uh, sorry everyone.
Just gonna need to
keep you here another 20
while we sweep the third.
Rhea, it's okay if we go back to ATN?
Thanks, yeah.
... within minutes.
They are now surrounding
this building, and to
catch our viewers up here
about ten minutes ago, at
least one shot was fired
inside the ATN offices,
along with screams.
You doin' okay?
Oh, um, well.
I'm finding it increasingly
difficult to explain to people
why I'm canceling and where I am.
And you were here
having a meeting with my dad
this afternoon, so...
Interesting.
It's just, uh... Just nonsense.
How come you're in?
You work here now?
Uh, no, I just, uh...
my family owns the joint.
I don't know if you knew that.
... no word on any number of casualties,
but we do know that there has
been at least one shot fired.
Not your favored style, huh?
Well, depends what you think news is.
A public utility, or
entertainment option.
You can actually do both.
Inform and engage.
Well, it's certainly full of vim.
Full of piss and vinegar.
I take it you're not
taking any offer seriously?
Actually, Shiv, we had
a productive meeting,
so maybe let me and Dad handle this.
Sorry. Excuse me. Clumsy old Shiv,
stomping all over it in my work boots.
It was a good chat, but I think
"hard no" was the take home.
There's no need to put a name on it.
Doesn't feel right to me either.
And we take her view very seriously,
what with her years of
media business experience.
I just can't see it.
Like, the thing for me is
that culturally, politically,
your operation, it's exactly
what we lack in the portfolio.
But I don't see how
the business side works.
Uh-huh. Well, I'd say the
business synergies are...
are obvious, you know.
One legal, finance, distribution,
marketing department.
I think it's the incompatible cultures
that... that stink up the deal.
Oh, uh, on that...
We did have one thing to
mention that could, uh,
- address that issue.
- Uh-huh?
Twenty-one billion dollars.
Okay. Well, look, I'm a mere conduit.
Well, maybe you should conduit that.
You know, I suppose the thing is,
it's an emotional
matter for the Pierces.
Money is not irrelevant,
but... but, how can I put it...
Relevant?
- Nevertheless...
- 21.5.
Kendall. I... Is he allowed
to just say numbers?
- Is that enough?
- It's not up to me,
so you're just bidding
against yourself there.
Look, I'm a hairy old
bastard who everybody hates,
yadda, yadda.
But I fuckin' love news,
and news people.
We can argue the angles,
but I will invest.
Well, it would take a
hell of a lot of investment
from where things are.
- Twenty-two billion.
- Jesus, Kendall.
Can he say that, Dad?
I mean that's not even the issue, right?
- Um, well...
- So... So what's the issue?
Editorial independence?
I don't think there's anything
to even say without that.
Well, okay, there are models,
right, for an independent board.
And forgetting the numbers,
there are structures designed
to ensure the current
philosophical approach
is protected.
Okay, thank you. And now, um...
remembering the numbers,
what would move the dial for them?
22.5?
Now, honestly, be careful
or I'll take you seriously.
Well, if the business side can work,
then I guess one pitch
for the family could be,
"Waystar isn't coming in to fuck you,
but to make sweet, sweet,
Barry White-investment love."
Beauty saved by the
beast would be the flavor.
I think it's telling that
your most positive spin
still sounds a bit rapey.
- Hey. Do you trust me?
- Do I trust you?
That's not really the issue, Dad.
I mean, you're not
gonna be around forever,
so there need to be structures in place
- that are...
- Siobhan. Please.
This is what it comes down to.
You know, we can draw up some agreement
with any number of provisions in it,
but you know that if I want,
I'll find a way round it.
So, in the end, it's a question, right?
If I say I won't fuck Pierce over,
I'll keep the brand, their
editors, their people,
do you trust me?
And will you tell them to trust me?
Uh-huh.
Because when I say
something will happen...
that thing will happen.
Am I right, kids?
- Right.
- Um, right.
So, will you tell 'em?
Twenty-four. And they can trust me.
I, um... I'm with him.
So is this the safe room?
Yes. Apparently it's impregnable.
Well, um, they announced
the winning pitch.
- Oh, they did?
- Uh-huh.
Are you attempting to
do suspense on me, Brian?
We won.
Oh, look at that. Great.
- You don't believe me?
- Mm, nope.
Do you happen to know who
they were going to give it to,
before they gave it to the name?
I don't think it was the name.
Well, that's very touching,
but I'm basically
fucking Elvis around here.
So you wanna go check?
Yeah. Yeah, let's fucking check.
Cool. Well, I'll be right back.
Hey, baby, how about
this for the eulogy?
- "Lester touched all of us."
- Okay, no.
I don't think you should do your speech.
No one else is gonna get here.
I have to. I said I would.
Baby, I think it could be
really bad for your campaign.
I mean, I was just talking
to those guys over there.
- The Wolf Pack?
- "The Wolf Pack"?
Yeah, Dad's old crew, back in the day.
Oh, Jesus. Okay,
some of the stuff that
they got up to with Mo,
- you do not want to be associated with.
- Sure, no. I know.
Still, it's complicated.
It was a different time.
But it wasn't a time before
they invented laws, was it?
I mean, what if this shit comes out,
and you're on the record
praising the shit out of him?
Oh, this is a nightmare.
Why can't I be the one caught
in a lockdown with a maniac?
Connor? Hi. Sorry to interrupt.
I'm Michelle Pantsil.
I'm working on a study...
I know who you are.
I... I spoke to Lester
a lot toward the end.
He always spoke so fondly of you.
Oh, I see you a mile away, sister.
What, you want to dig
through my treasure chest
for some previous memory gems?
No, I don't want to make anyone
do anything they don't want to do.
Hey, if you wanna print
something in your little book,
you may print the following line:
"Connor Roy was interested in politics
at a very young age."
That's it.
Connor. C... This isn't an interview.
We're just two people
chatting at a funeral.
- Fine.
- It's a good turnout.
It's a nice church, don't you think?
Tell you what a nice church it is,
"Connor Roy was interested in
politics from a very young age."
Okay. You know you're not
doing yourself any favors
by refusing to talk?
Interesting point, to which I would add:
"Connor Roy was interested in
politics from a very young age."
I look forward to hearing what
you have to say about Lester.
Come on.
Okay, folks. We're all clear.
- Is he still in there?
- I don't know.
God.
You know, uh, Greg, I know that, um...
it wasn't cool, you know.
The bottles, the attack.
No, it didn't feel great.
I don't always like who I am, Greg.
Yeah, I get that.
But don't you think it
might be just the right time
for me to make a move?
Seriously, Greg?
You're smart, you're
ambitious, you're loyal.
Why would I let you go? Come on.
Okay, wait. I have a thing,
but I... I'm reluctant to say.
- What do you mean?
- I...
I just... I have some leverage,
but I'm reluctant to use it.
You know, in case it
sours things for us.
What leverage, Greg?
I just... Um...
Well, I'm not bringing this
up as any form of threat,
but...
So, you know
when you had me destroy
those documents at Cruises?
No.
Well, I... I kept it...
I kept a few of them.
Just in case I got in trouble,
and 'cause I was worried
that maybe I was destroying
evidence of criminality.
Did you now?
So, like, I don't know. Would it be...
I don't wanna bring anything up to you
in a way that feels, like, horrible,
but would be bad for me to,
like, mention those to you now?
Are you asking if you can blackmail me?
No... No, I... I would...
I would hate that.
I like you, it's just,
you know, context.
Very well. I accept your blackmail.
No, I'm not blackmailing you,
- Tom. No...
- But you are, though,
- you piece of shit. Greg...
- I'm not!
... I'm gonna accelerate you. Okay?
New title. Ton more
money, nice new office.
You're moving up, you can
throw away the training bra.
Seat at the big table. You like that?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. I like that.
You fucking... Look at you.
Where are they, those papers?
I'll never tell.
You're a fuckin' slime ball!
- No.
- Attaboy.
For I am persuaded that
neither death nor life,
nor angels, nor principalities,
nor powers, nor things present,
nor things to come, nor height,
- nor depth...
- Here you go. I did a pass.
Let's see her try to make
something out of this.
... from the love of God,
which is in Christ Jesus,
- our Lord.
- Amen.
Hello.
I'm here as a fellow human
to acknowledge that Lester
has, as we know, passed on.
Lester was a man.
Also, Lester was an employee
of the Waystar company
for 40 years.
And when a man dies, it is sad.
All of us will die one day.
In this case, it is
Lester who has done so.
Lester was alive for 78 years.
But no more.
Now he is dead.
Lester's wife is Maria. They
were married for 15 years.
Now she is sad.
Apparently he emailed a
close friend last week,
talking of a culture of bullying.
It's a newsroom, not
a fucking kindergarten.
Again, condolences.
As the head of an organization myself,
I can only imagine how
you must be feeling.
- It's a dark day.
- A lot of introspection ahead.
Perhaps we could talk again next week.
Thanks for your hospitality.
Hope to see you soon.
Well, if not, we'll always
have the panic room.
I'll let them know that number.
And that they can trust me.
I will give them my honest assessment.
And, uh, if you're really serious about
approaching the family,
do yourself a favor.
A peace offering would be nice.
That Walmart Mussolini
who puts Nan Pierce
off her Old Fashioned, Ravenhead, yes?
Well done, son.
Good work.
I fucking killed it, Tabs.
I slaughtered them, and you know what?
They're jealous. And that's
just all there is to it.
They are jealous. Um,
anyway, how are you?
I'm good. I'm, uh, yeah. I'm
about to get into the bath.
Oh, yeah? Um, yeah. Okay.
Do you want to, uh...
You wanna do this or what?
We got like six weeks of this.
Yeah, sure. Um, okay.
So, I am making the bath really sudsy.
Is that because you're a dirty one?
I am. I'm a dirty, dirty girl.
Yeah, you are.
And I would love to fuck you.
Would you?
I'm so wet for you right now.
Um, that's not... Uh, you
don't have to be so specific.
I'm being sexy.
Yeah, it's just... Could you not
do that thing with your voice?
It's, like, breathy and unnatural.
That's what I sound like
when I'm turned on, Roman.
I know, it's just... I just
don't like it, you know.
It's just, like... Let's
just be normal. More like,
"I wanna fuck you in the pussy."
Hmm. Okay. Well, I was...
I was trying to get into it,
but, you know.
Okay. No, fine. You're
right. Sorry. Um...
I'm fucking you. I'm...
I'm fucking you hard.
Amazing.
What are you gonna do next?
You gonna, I don't know,
change your water filter cartridge?
Ah, Jesus fucking Christ...
Oh! Oh, I'm coming! I'm coming!
Ah, I came. Yay. Thank
you. Hooray. Bye. Thanks!
A feeling of hopelessness
has set in for those watching from afar,
leading many to wonder,
what is the best way to explain
this tragedy to children?
Pierce News contributor
David Stanton joins us.
David, first off, are we...
Roman, what is it now?
You know, I'm still pissed
off they didn't give me
- any good footage.
- Seriously?
They're treating me
like I'm a piece of shit.
- You are a piece of shit.
- Fuck you.
I found a rough diamond out here
and I wanna bring him back
with me. Fast track him.
Also, we should build my ride, bitch.
I'll email you. It's genius.
No, no. We are not building
a ride that you came up with
on your first day of
management training, Roman.
Well, you should. I
am an ideas fountain.
You're acting like an
over-excited little boy.
You know, technically,
I'm your fuckin' boss.
Go to bed, Roman. Go to bed,
and masturbate all your ideas out,
and let's see how
excited you feel tomorrow.
Well, maybe. Maybe I will.
Maybe I'll just leave you on the pillow
so you can hear my brilliance cascading.
Fine. I've heard plenty worse
than a spoiled brat
ejaculating on himself.
Oh, yeah? You sure about that?
I could be doing it
now for all you know.
Well, get going. Chop chop.
You disgusting little pig.
You're pathetic.
You are a revolting
little worm, aren't you?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I am.
You little slime puppy.
Yes. Yeah, what else am I?
You're revolting, Roman.
Yes. Yeah.
Only you can be trusted
with the meds, huh?
Yeah. Till we have a system going on.
Mm-hmm. So here's a question.
What the fuck is going
on between you and Dad?
What do you mean?
Do you have something on
him? Are you blackmailing Dad?
No. I'm... I'm... I don't know...
We're... We're just in, uh...
We're just in a good...
good place these days.
Uh-huh?
All right. Do you have a deal with him?
Did he make you an
offer in the Hamptons?
Um, no. No, Shiv.
There's... There's no deal.
I promise you.
Then what? Why's he protecting you?
Protecting me?
Yeah, the drugs, the shoplifting,
the... the fucking... the takeover bid.
Yeah, I'm not sure what you mean.
Uh-huh.
Anyway, why do you care so much?
You know, what... what is
this? What's going on here?
- You comin' in?
- Can we just talk?
I'm not a fucking dummy.
There is an atmosphere.
Uh...
Yeah, I don't know. He's... He's just...
Maybe, uh, he's concerned
about me, for whatever reason.
Yeah? For whatever reason?
You'd need to ask him.
You can't tell me? You can't
tell me what's going on?
No.
Fucking look at me.
Shiv. It's not gonna be me.
Right. You wanna tell me why?
Come here. Give me a hug.
- Come here.
- Give you a hug?
Hey.
You okay?
I would just ask that
you take care of me,
because, uh, if Dad
didn't need me right now
I don't exactly know...
what I would be for.
You wanna talk some more?
I r... I really can't.
But, uh...
thank you.
Yeah, it ain't gonna be me.
Backing Pierce is the
key to our proxy defense.
They're inquiring about
your moral character,
hence this weekend.
My worry is that Kendall
may come across as too cool
and likable.
Welcome to Turnhaven,
our city on the hill.
Wow, I like this staff. Why
couldn't this staff be Dad?
Any thought given to whom
you might handover the keys?
Just whisper it in my ear.
Watching you people melt down
is the most satisfying activity.
We aim to please.