- Welcome to the family.
- Yeah, I'm finally in.
- Your sister's just in for the day.
- Oh yeah?
Just to observe.
Rhea, we got her.
The family trusts her.
You get her on board, that's huge.
I want Pierce.
But it only works for me fast.
On behalf of the Pierce family,
the message would be a
typically balanced, nuanced
- and objective fuck off.
- (GUNFIRE)
- MAN: Shooter!
- Excuse me, excuse me!
- What's going on?
- We just want to get you safe.
Where's Kendall? Is he safe?
ATN segment producer. It was a suicide.
We did have one thing to mention.
Twenty-four billion dollars.
And they can trust me.
Would it be okay for me to
maybe go to another department?
- (YELLING)
- Stop pelting me!
- Security!
You're not building a
ride that you came up with
on your first day of
management training, Roman.
Technically I'm your fucking boss.
Go to bed and masturbate
all your ideas out.
- Maybe I will.
- You disgusting little pig.
What the fuck is going
on between you and dad?
- Did he make you an offer?
- It's not going to be me.
♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
- (HORNS BLARING)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SHIV ROY BREATHES DEEPLY)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
Thanks, Richard.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
SHIV: Hey!
- TOM: Hey!
- Hi!
TOM: Hey, how are you? You made it!
- How was London?
- Yeah. (KISSES)
- Good. Yeah.
- Yeah? You okay?
SHIV: Yeah, I'm fine. Uh...
Where's... Is Ken here? Is...
- Uh... I don't know!
- Is Rom?
I don't know. So, are...
you okay? What did you do?
- Who did you see?
- Uh... Yeah, it was a blur.
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
I'm just preoccupied.
Okay. But you don't think that...
- What?
- You don't think it could be
- today that he...
- What?
- ... might announce you?
- No.
But...
Yeah, you know, full family
briefing pre-departure
to the Pierces', where...
it would be smart to have
someone to announce, so...
- Yes.
- Yeah.
Okay. Well, why didn't you say, honey?
Because it probably isn't,
so would you relax? It's...
I am relaxed. I'm just excited.
Richard! Hail, my fellow toilerman.
I have returned from real America,
bearing the gift of sight.
- SHIV: How was summer camp?
- Hmm? What's that?
Didn't catch that. I've been
down in the salt mines so long
with my fellow Johnny Lunchpails,
I no longer speak One-Percent.
SHIV: Mm, Roman, you were
slinging candy apples,
not digging the Panama Canal.
ROMAN ROY: I've seen the world
for how it really is, Siobhan,
and it has changed me.
I'm a kettle corn shoveler,
here to show you frilly
clit-flickers the truth. Hi!
MARCIA ROY: Mm.
ROMAN: Mwah! Hey, Con.
How's the hooker with the heart of gold?
... and, you know, I think
that could be a way in.
(CHUCKLES) Ho! Hello! Thanks, all. Um...
Cars are waiting. But
first, some announcements.
- Frank.
- So, as you know,
the good news is that the
Pierces are entertaining
our offer, but, bad news,
they're inquiring about
your moral character,
hence this weekend.
LOGAN ROY: They all wanna
look us in the teeth.
Right. They want our 24 billion,
but they also wanna be able
to ensure the integrity
of their news outlets
- into the future.
- LOGAN: And I want an onion
to taste like a fucking peach,
- but there you go.
- (FRANK VERNON LAUGHS)
Before we waste a weekend,
can I just check
why this time is gonna
be different, Dad?
Lack of readership.
PGM is getting
outflanked left and right.
The whole edifice is crumbling.
Oof! Well, that just
screams, "Bye, bye, bye!"
(INHALES) I... I'm kidding. I get it.
FRANK: Even Nan, the queen
bee, is feeling the squeeze.
The Pierce Family Trust has fractured.
So, to ensure that
everything goes smoothly,
we have prepared a few do's
and don'ts for the weekend.
Oh, so, what, don't
shit in the soup tureen?
Topics to stay clear of:
Ravenhead, ATN, Israel,
Brightstar, and Cruise's rumor mill.
- GERRI KILLMAN: Mm.
- Steer onto gossip, investments,
art, movies... Tittle-tattle.
Wider cultural interests.
Well, what if your
wider cultural interest
is hate-jerking to Instagram?
Just asking for a friend.
Ooh, me! She's talking about me.
FRANCIS: What else?
Oh, two drinks maximum.
Not big drinkers.
That's okay. Nobody here has any
glaring substance abuse issues
that almost brought
down the company, right?
Tom, we may have to shake you up
a little, push you around a bit.
- Uh-huh?
- GERRI: They hate ATN,
- they hate our papers.
- LOGAN: You're the strawman
for the sins of ATN. Cane
your haunches a bit, okay?
Okay. Uh-huh. Could we...
Could we may... perhaps...
- put the responsibility on Syd?
- No, no, no, no.
I know what you're
saying, but no. We, uh...
We need to wear the hair
shirt, call you a shitbag,
and say that we never watch. Right?
Okay. Got it. Hair shirt.
LOGAN: Rhea and I will
handle the big picture.
Uh, remind me again, does
Rhea work for the company?
Uh, remind us, do you?
I'm just asking if we
really wanna entrust
the fate of our company
to another company's CEO.
- We can trust Rhea.
- SHIV: Okay. We don't know Rhea.
- I know Rhea.
- Who the fuck is Rhea?
- SHIV: Exactly.
- Guys, what dad is saying
is, just know your
role and execute, okay?
Well, my worry is that Kendall
may come across as too cool and likable.
LOGAN: Thanks for all your help.
We need this. Bagging Pierce
is the key to our proxy defense.
And the defense is life itself.
See you at Plymouth Rock.
- You okay?
- Yeah. An hour late,
and make no secret where you've been.
- KENDALL ROY: Yeah, we're good.
- And, uh,
keep clean this weekend, eh, killer?
- ROMAN: Richard...
- (ELEVATOR DINGS)
- Oh! Sorry about it. After you.
- No, please.
Yep. Chivalry is not...
You know. (MUMBLES)
- Shit before the shovel.
- ROMAN: Allow me to be the shit.
- LOGAN: Pinkie!
- SHIV: Yeah.
Let them take care
of the bottom-feeders.
- We work on Nan.
- Uh-huh. Okay.
- Good cop, misogynist cop?
- Ah, well, sure.
You know, the woman thing? (CHUCKLES)
- (CHUCKLES) Yeah. Well, yeah.
- They like your politics.
Okay. Uh-huh. Yeah.
I know you don't like this buy.
No, no, I... You know,
I can see the logic. Yeah.
- I guess.
- Good, good.
Anyway, my baby soon.
Hmm.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
♪ Succession 2x05 ♪
Tern Haven
So, how's it going? The course?
Oh. Um, it's actually, you
know, I mean, it's bullshit,
but it's good. Yeah.
Ah, well, I'm proud of you,
son. Getting back in there.
Thank you, Dad.
But this weekend, don't mention it.
Sounds like you're back
in business kindergarten.
Right. Thank you.
Everybody smile.
- I am smiling.
- Yeah, not like a pervert.
ROMAN: Wow, Jesus. Check
out fucking Papa Smurf.
Oh, this is too fucking weird already.
- (LAUGHS)
- NAN PIERCE: St. Francis of Assisi!
Are you ready for the rummage sale?
(LAUGHS) You've brought me animals!
Oh, welcome to Ternhaven,
our city on the hill.
- Nan Pierce.
- LOGAN: Pleasure.
I suppose you've been
waiting for this moment
for quite a while,
haven't you, greedy-guts?
- (LAUGHS) Well...
- (LAUGHS) Teasing. Teasing!
Well, uh, thank you for
inviting us to your home.
Well, I think we're gonna
have fun getting a look
at all of you, won't we?
Uh, Nan, stop blabbing
and let us at the canapés!
(LAUGHTER)
Come, come homeward. Promises to keep,
and miles to go before
we sleep. (LAUGHS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
SHIV: Hello, lovely to meet
you. I've heard a lot about you.
MARNIE PIERCE: Connor,
I'm Marnie. Very nice...
CONNOR ROY: Pleasure.
- MARNIE: Welcome.
- RHEA JARRELL: Nice to meet you.
GABRIEL PIERCE: Gabriel.
Nice to meet you.
SHIV: Shiv.
- EDUARDO: Hello, Eduardo
- SHIV: We've met before.
LOGAN: So, how are we looking?
Issue?
RHEA: Naomi has flown in
from Marin, which is...
a nice surprise.
What does that do to the math, then?
Does she... Does she have
a share? What does it mean?
RHEA: Well, it complicates it.
So, why wasn't I prepared for this?
Um... Because it's not my fucking job?
- And ask your people?
- So?
RHEA: She usually sits these things out.
- She has major juice with Nan.
- Could we do it without Nan?
- Marnie!
- MARNIE: Yes?
RHEA: Hey. You, me and a martini, now!
- Oh, yes!
- (RHEA LAUGHS, MURMURS)
- (PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Um... Oh.
Oh... Penis cat.
- ROMAN: Mm. "This wine is triumphant"?
- _
- GERRI: Uh...
- ROMAN: No?
- "Your vagina trumpets."
- GERRI: Shh.
It's, uh, "I triumph in the truth."
Oh! Right, of course, truth.
Love it. It's the best, right?
Truth. He seems cool.
Everyone. I promise not to
interrupt your tipple for long,
but I just wanted to take a brief moment
to welcome you to our funny little house
and to let our guests know
that what you're drinking is
Hank Pierce's Break Bumper!
ALL: The Break Bumper!
The recipe is still,
and no-one believes,
from the wallet of
Teddy Roosevelt's valet.
- (NAN LAUGHS)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- NAN: Cheers, everyone. Cheers.
- ALL: Cheers.
NAN: Welcome.
- MARK PIERCE: Oh.
- NAN: Mm! So...
Yeah, I'm actually getting
my second PhD right now in...
- Oh!
- ... Africana Studies from Brown.
Wow! So you'll be a double doctor?
(LAUGHS) Well, the
second PhD is much harder.
Yeah, five years is
an absolute gauntlet.
SHIV: Oh, I'm sure.
But just think, yeah,
once you're done, you won't
have to waste the twelve seconds
it takes to look up
something on Wikipedia.
- (TOM LAUGHS)
- SHIV: But seriously, though,
you know, well done.
It's quite an achievement.
MARK: Yeah, thank you.
- Connor Roy!
- Mm-hmm.
- Maxim Pierce. (LAUGHS)
- Hi.
- The man who would be king, hmm?
- (LAUGHS)
Don Quixote of Iowa,
tilting at straw polls!
Yep. I've got a big old tent,
and everyone's welcome.
- (BOTH LAUGH)
- So, uh, are you in politics?
Sort of. Brookings Institute.
Ah, Brookings! Yes, of course,
a fine, elite establishment.
Oh, I didn't take you for a fan!
I thought you were on the whole
"abolish the federal reserve",
"fluoride is poison",
pissing in jars end of things.
Uh, no, I'm actually on the
liberty and justice for all
end of things, but
hey, different strokes!
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
ROMAN: Mm. Here comes
Ken. Spiraling down.
(LAUGHS) Uh, Rom, you remember Naomi?
Ah! Yeah, that's right!
From the... From the thing.
- TABITHA: Yeah.
- NAOMI PIERCE: Oh, the thing.
Where you tried to
order my family's legacy
over the phone, like an Uber Eats.
- Of course.
- (CHUCKLES) Burn.
- NAOMI: How are you?
- That's the thing.
Uh, you know, I'm well. I'm very well.
I'm working real hard, you know.
- Yeah? Hmm.
- Yeah, no. Not at all, really.
Maybe. Who knows.
What he meant to say is
that he's really passionate
about maintaining the integrity
of the customer-facing brands.
- Wow.
- (TABITHA LAUGHS)
NAN: You have an interesting family.
LOGAN: Yeah, I apologize
for the lateness of my son.
- Oh, well.
- He's been volunteering.
Really? That's impressive.
He has the time, even in the
teeth of a takeover battle?
- Well...
- He's very capable.
- A lot of bandwidth.
- (MARCIA LAUGHS)
Oh, it's wonderful to
have such bandwidth,
after everything that... You know.
Uh... No, thank you, I'm...
Rosa! Rosa, have a drink with us.
Oh, I have to finish the dinner, Miss.
NAN: No, I know, but just...
just one. You can take a break,
- can't you?
- But dinner.
Well... All right. All right.
You never treat yourself.
LOGAN: Ah. Kendall!
Hi! You made it! (LAUGHS)
Ah, we missed you, son.
KENDALL: Thanks, Dad. Yeah.
I, uh... missed you too.
Uh, are you all right
for targeting Peter?
Uh, you know, shove a bar of
gold down his fucking throat?
Yeah, sure. Got it. Good.
(TAPPING GLASS)
LOGAN: Pardon me,
um... As my family knows
only too well, I am... I ain't
no master of the speechifying,
but I would, uh... I would
just like to thank the Pierces
for their hospitality. Um...
Like Romans amongst you Greeks,
I'm sure you find us all
rather, you know, big, vulgar,
and boisterous. (CHUCKLES)
We... We appreciate your forbearance.
And, uh, well, you know,
as an old news man,
I'd be remiss if I... if
I didn't commend all of you
for your stewardship of PGM,
because wherever we are
on the political spectrum,
we can all agree,
for decade after decade,
your outlets have been essential
to the functioning
of our grand republic.
- Long may they so remain.
- SHIV: Hear, hear.
- NAN: Hear, hear.
- ALL: Hear, hear.
He would like to kill and shit on you!
(LAUGHS)
Wow, I like this Dad. Why
couldn't this Dad be Dad?
Eh. You clean up nice.
How are you?
Uh... I'm good. Good.
How are you really?
Um... Uh... You know.
Yeah, I know. I know.
It's good to see you.
- We could use the help.
- Oh, "we"?
Mm-hmm. You, them, us. Whatever.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
ROMAN: I think it's great.
Of course it's going well.
I mean, no-one's fucked Nan
or killed her cat by accident,
so I think we're doing pretty good.
- LOGAN: Yeah, I know, I know.
- ROMAN: Have you seen that guy?
Excuse me.
What the fuck did you say to Mark?
- Making cracks about his PhD?
- Well, it was a joke!
- He laughed.
- FRANK: Yeah, it seemed
- he did not enjoy that.
- He's a yes, Shiv! He's solid!
Why are you even bothering with him?
- Have we lost sight of Maxim?
- Who's on Maxim?
Me, and I just have to
say, if he contradicts
any more planks in my
political philosophy,
I'm gonna piss in his Break Bumper.
Hey! Hey, he's leaning "no sale".
Cut the horseshit, know your role.
- Yeah, Pa.
- LOGAN: And, uh, Shiv,
I want you on Nan.
Okay, Dad, we don't
have to be so schematic.
LOGAN: Romulus.
When you laugh, please
do it at the same volume
as everyone else.
We didn't get you from a hyena farm.
- Thanks, Pop.
- The good news is that Nan
already seems to be spending
the money in her head,
but she can still be
swayed by her family,
so every cousin counts.
Oh, I think Marnie might
be leaning "sell", so...
Marnie isn't a problem. Now, everybody,
stay in your lanes. Who's on Peter?
Yeah, I got it, Dad.
Oh, oh, you got it? I'm
so impressed. Shut up.
Okay, a bit of Lincoln
Center chat, okay?
He's worried that we're barbarians.
- And Naomi.
- ROMAN: Yeah.
- Hit Naomi!
- Got it.
ROMAN: Okay, onwards.
SHIV: Can't stand up to Maxim?
ROMAN: Tabs, you gonna help me on that?
- He's an asshole!
- SHIV: What part of your policy
- was he "not right now"?
- CONNOR: No, no, no, no, no.
No, everything. He's dismissing.
- Well, nice work so far.
- MARCIA: Merci beaucoup.
I'm very excited to be getting top marks
along with your other pupils.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
MAXIM: ... conservative, or are they...
ROMAN: Excellent work.
Thank you so much.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
TABITHA: Yeah. How
many breakers you had?
MAN: Whoa, whoa!
- (APPLAUSE)
- CONNOR: Bravo.
NAN: Oh, stop!
Now...
Grace.
(NAN CLEARS HER THROAT)
I'm afraid we've gone
so Unitarian out here
that we've given up on poor Jesus,
and we have started
worshipping Shakespeare!
(SCATTERED LAUGHTER)
Your scepter.
(INHALES) Hmm.
The purest treasure...
mortal time affords
is spotless reputation.
That away, men are but gilded loam,
or painted clay.
Mine honor is my life; both grow in one.
Take honor from me, and my life is done.
- MAN: Wow.
- (APPLAUSE)
NAN: Soup's on, people.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hey, that was awesome.
- I'm Kendall.
- I know. Naomi.
Yeah, I know.
So, uh, are you, like, a...
- an actress or like a poetess?
- NAOMI: Oh... (LAUGHS)
Or something? Because
that was pretty legit.
Oh, I, uh, volunteer
at a drug addiction treatment
center in Mill Valley,
and I continue my
recovery there as well.
Oh. Oh, wow. That... That's great. I...
Yeah, I'm actually in recovery myself.
- I know.
- Okay. (CHUCKLES)
My not-so-spotless
reputation precedes me.
- (LAUGHS) No, I could just tell.
- KENDALL: Really?
Oh, okay. Right.
I'd like to have three novels
and a memoir going at once.
- It's like natural selection.
- Oh, brother, I hear that.
- Are you a reader?
- Me? Oh, big time. Yeah.
Can you recommend anything
that Oprah isn't pushing?
- Any new fiction?
- (LAUGHS) Right?
Oh! Uh, yeah, sure, I can. Um...
I rather enjoyed The Electric Circus.
- The Electric Circus.
- Mm-hmm.
- MARNIE: Who's the author?
- What was that? What?
- Who's the author?
- ROMAN: Oh! Oh, gosh.
I wanna say... Shit. Who was
it? It was, oh... Timothy Lipton.
SHIV: Uh-huh? What's it about? Rom?
Uh, what's The Electric Circus about?
- Uh-huh.
- It is about a young man
making his way through the world,
except in two different time periods.
It kind of switches
back and forth between...
The circus part is
a, you know, metaphor.
For what?
ROMAN: For the anxiety
of modern life, Siobhan.
MARNIE: I'm not seeing it on Google.
You said it's called
"The Electric Circus"?
Yeah. I thou... I mean, shit.
Is it The Electric Circus?
Well, I think it's called...
CONNOR: That's all very
interesting, but let's just
- agree to disagree, shall we?
- Sure! (LAUGHS)
(LAUGHS) Well, that's just
the sort of expert analysis
I'd expect from a deep-state
wonk with both lips
firmly glued to the Soros teat.
Oh, well, you can't change Washington
without knowing Washington
I mean, can you name me
one member of the House
Commerce Committee?
Oh, uh, yeah, I think I know one.
Uh, Representative
Ferdinand D. Who-Gives-A-Shit
from the great state
of No-One-Fucking-Cares.
Well, I'm convinced. I
mean, clear some space
on Mount Rushmore, folks! (LAUGHS)
CONNOR: Yeah, yeah, well...
NAN: I actually thought
you said the wrecking ball.
(LAUGHTER)
(DISTANT LAUGHTER)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
SHIV: I just wanted to say, I'm, uh...
What you're doing, the
PhDs, I think it's great.
- I'm sorry if I...
- MARK: No, no! It was a hit,
- a very palpable hit!
- (LAUGHS)
(LAUGHS) I can take a joke.
Oh, right. Because it
was a joke. (LAUGHS)
Of course.
Are you pleased to be
out of politics, Siobhan?
Oh, yes, I am. I'm getting over
it like a nasty stomach bug.
- Mm-hmm.
- It can be a dirty business.
Made dirtier by a certain
cable news behemoth.
- Oh, come on, Rhea, let's play nice now.
- RHEA: Oh?
We can discuss the white nationalist
elephant in the room, can't we?
Tug on its trunk a bit?
I'm not operationally involved.
(LAUGHS) Come on.
No, no, no, I let my
people do their own thing.
I mean, if you... If you
wanna talk ATN, you know,
Tom's the barbarian.
(LAUGHS) Hi, hello, I'm the...
right-wing ogre at your service.
(LAUGHTER)
NAOMI: Wait, you don't
even believe your own stuff?
Well, I've always wanted to
balance Waystar's portfolio
with, um...
with... voice...
- From the left?
- Well, no. Pierce isn't...
Your people just follow the
truth, wherever it leads, right?
Oh, well, you know, our
people are just hacks.
- (LAUGHTER)
- Oh!
- But we like 'em.
- Come on! (LAUGHS)
I mean, I guess our... our people
try to follow the truth, too, Shiv.
You give them what they need,
we give them what they want.
We make a good match.
Of course. Right. No, Dad...
I think we, Dad, just wants
a bigger tent, a bigger pie.
It means more profit,
and then more investment.
So, I suppose that just
makes me a prim little matron,
if I object to being fumbled
by the invisible hand of the market?
Th... That's... No.
That's not what I meant. I...
Sure, a fair exchange
isn't exactly robbery,
and money does allegedly
make the world go round, so...
Money? Money is a social construct,
whereas virtue, integrity,
these things actually exist.
Well, the... Just... Well,
because just this morning,
I went to the store, and
I bought a pound of ham,
and I paid for it by, you know,
telling them I was really worried
about the environment.
(LAUGHTER)
SHIV: Don't mind Tom, he
finds other people's integrity
a personal affront, for some reason.
(LAUGHS) Well, yes, that's...
Thank you, I'm a piece of dirt.
- (LAUGHTER)
- Oh, yep. Yep. I'll take it.
SHIV: Right! (LAUGHS)
Wait a minute, but Tom, Tom,
if there was an acquisition,
then, as head of news,
you would be the guy in charge
of our crown jewels, right?
Oh, well, we'd have to see about that.
Ooh! Hear that, Tom?
Sounds dicey. Got a pitch?
Tom, everything rests on
what you're about to say.
- (LAUGHTER)
- NAN: Oh, lay off him!
Oh, wait a minute,
though. I didn't hear.
So, would he stay on
as the head of news?
- I...
- Ooh, king of edible leaves,
His Majesty, the spinach.
Look, I just, uh... I think there's...
The business, the journalistic values...
- Mm-hmm.
- There's a lot of admirers in this family.
That's all.
Uh, like all recent
converts, Shiv is a zealot.
TOM: (LAUGHS) I think what
we can all agree on is that
it's great for people to
communicate, of whatever stripe.
I think it was Thoreau
who said of the telegraph,
"Maine may speak to Texas,
but what if they have nothing
- to say to one another?
- (LAUGHTER)
That should be engraved into
the bezel of every iPhone
- in the world.
- NAN: Oh!
- Hear, hear! The bezel.
- Have you spoken to Shirley?
I'm so sorr... Will you excuse
us for two seconds? I'm so worried
- about our... It's a...
- SHIV: Our dog, Mondale.
It's a dog thing. So silly. Sorry to...
SHIV: Is very ill at the moment.
TOM: Arthritis. We think it's arthritis.
- NAN: So sorry.
- TOM: His hips.
SHIV: Excuse us. Sorry.
They have a dog. A dog named Mondale.
- PETER: Oh!
- That's helpful, right?
PETER: Yeah, it is.
This is... This is what happens.
You get given the keys to the castle,
and then you get paralyzed,
staring into the eyes of the cobra.
You're riding me pretty hard in there.
- (SIGHS)
- You think I should
- fight back more?
- You know, and then,
he smells the vacillation,
and then he's just...
He's got you. You're done.
He's juiced another lemon.
It would be nice if you
stopped beating up on me too.
- What?
- Maybe you could stop
- beating up on me too.
- What? What do...
That's just nothing. That's silly.
- What... No-one cares.
- Well, technically, I care.
- I care.
- Well, sometimes you say
stupid things. You know, he's
got me second-guessing myself.
I'm wavering on the best
strategy for landing a deal
that I don't even like.
- I really want this!
- I know.
Really, I wanna be
sitting at that table.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- (BREATHES TREMULOUSLY)
Listen to me.
You are sitting at the table.
You are.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
I'm good. Mm-hmm. Let's go.
TABITHA: They're trying to
adopt. You know, the list is,
like, insane, so I'm thinking,
like, if they can't have a baby
in six months, I'm just gonna,
you know, offer them my womb.
Why not? I'm young, I'm hardy.
MARNIE: I have a friend who
did that. It was so great.
- TABITHA: Mm.
- Uh, but if it's not too rude to ask,
then what about you two?
TABITHA: Oh, you mean us having
a baby? No, we're not planning
- to have a baby, because...
- Oop.
... that would require us having sex.
- Whoa! Hey now.
- PETER: I'm so sorry.
- I don't mean to pry.
- Oh, yes you did.
No, no, no, no. It's
totally fine. That's just...
That's, like, not how we
do it. It's not our thing.
We're kind of like eunuch besties.
- Well, I wouldn't say that.
- It works for us.
It's a joke, obviously.
She's kidding. We're actually
quite relentless in that
regard. Just Fuck City.
- (PUNCHES PALM)
- Bingo, bango, bongo.
TABITHA: Anyway, you
don't have any kids, right?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- Refreshed?
- Oh? Uh...
Yeah. Yep, you bet.
NAN: Marcia, so, so tell me.
You... You grew up in Beirut.
What was that like?
LOGAN: Well, she... She doesn't
really like to talk about it.
Or you don't like to ask about it.
Well, um... when we first
met, the first or second night,
we stayed up all night, um...
And she told me her whole life story.
If I had a year, I couldn't
tell you my whole life.
- LOGAN: Uh-huh. Fine.
- Interesting.
Another glass for both of you?
Well, now, we tend to
kind of keep it to...
Yes, thank you.
LOGAN: Excuse me?
His cellar is all New World,
and it doesn't suit me.
Well, why didn't you say?
It suits you, so it can suit me.
See? I'm not a difficult person.
- Uh-huh.
- NAN: Well, as long as
the fat is being chewed,
I suppose I would be remiss
not to mention that
you're being targeted
for acquisition yourself, correct?
Oh, oh, that. Well, that's...
(CHUCKLES) You know, that's all over.
- Well, alas.
- Sandy's not well.
Syphilis, if you can believe it.
LOGAN: Uh. I... Yeah. I never...
I never believed that the takeover bid
- was real to begin with.
- Hmm. A Potemkin pillage.
(LAUGHS)
Oh, look, I have to ask.
The internal differences.
- Have they been smoothed over?
- Oh, very much so.
And any thought given to whom
you might hand over the keys?
Why, Madam, that is very forward.
And you're no fun.
We're all friends here now, aren't we?
Well, uh...
Gerri is on the paperwork as a stopgap,
but even she'd be the first
to admit that she couldn't
really do the job.
Well, maybe the second to admit.
(LAUGHTER)
Uh... There is a name.
But, you know, I really don't
like to deal in hypotheticals.
Ooh. He's an enigma.
- LOGAN: Well, one day.
- RHEA: What a tease, folks.
- Just whisper it in my ear.
- You know, I'll start to think
I'm not wanted.
(CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHING) Just... You can...
Well, you know, uh...
Oh, for fuck's sake, Dad, just
tell them it's gonna be me.
- NAN: Is that so?
- That is so.
- Roman, what's happening?
- Mm. My life just ended.
It's been discussed, um,
but I don't think we're quite
- at the point where, uh...
- No, not any time soon.
We've, uh... We've
discussed the transition
- and some arrangements.
- We won't bore you.
No! (LAUGHS) But I though we
could tell you all, though,
as friends.
PETER: Yeah. You know, maybe this dinner
was a little bit premature.
Seems like you guys
are still working some things out.
No, no, Peter, don't worry,
this is just family hijinks,
- as usual. We're good.
- Is that true?
- (SHOUTING) Will you stop?
- (LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
Well, anyway, I, um...
I was just thinking,
it is such a beautiful,
clear night out. Uh...
- Mark...
- MARK: Huh.
- NAN: Mark?
- I said, "Huh". (CHUCKLES)
Would you like to guide us on
a little after-dinner stargaze?
Uh, stargaze? I would love
to show you our little corner
- of the sky. (LAUGHS)
- NAN: (LAUGHS) Marvelous.
Boots for everyone, not to worry.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- TABITHA: Mm. Did you know?
- Uh, no. No, I did not know.
(FLICKING GLASS)
Shall we?
(SHIV BREATHING HEAVILY)
Keep in mind that I got
my PhD at Columbia in '89,
so I'm not what Whitman would
call a "learned astronomer".
(LAUGHS)
MARK: Right? No, but... So, I wish
I could show you through, uh...
Through a telescope,
but our naked eyes...
- Having fun?
- Oh, sure.
- I am having fun.
- NAOMI: (SCOFFS) Me too.
- KENDALL: You too?
- Watching you people melt down
is the most deeply satisfying
activity on planet Earth.
Oh, yeah? Uh-huh.
- Thank you.
- Sure. You got it.
We, uh... We aim to please.
No, I... feel quite redundant.
I mean, I came here to
fuck any deal, but...
it seems you all have just
fucked it yourselves, so...
So...
are you gonna ask me?
Ask you what?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Would you like to do some
illegal drugs with me?
- Yes, I would.
- Good. This way.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
SHIV: Okay, goodnight.
TOM: (BREATHING HEAVILY)
Jeepers-fucking-creepers,
what a shit-piñata. That was like...
That was like the most
Roy thing I have ever seen.
It's like I got a quart of
Roy injected into my eyeballs.
- (GRUNTS) Is there booze?
- Are you kidding?
No, it's just Emily Dickinson
and low-thread-count sheets.
- Shiv, what...
- (SIGHING)
What even was that?
Explain the chess move.
I... I don't know. I just... I
just... I just fucking said it.
- You just said it? No plan?
- No, not really. I...
I guess I thought, you know, "Fuck him.
Fuck him for stringing me along!"
Just, you know, shit or get off the pot.
Right. Right?
But, you know, I guess I didn't
really think that so much as...
As, you know, just...
Oh, Jesus Christ, my head.
Because I'm not sure how
much love there is for me
in a... as a sort of independent-of-you
sort of person. You know?
(SIGHS) Yeah, my dad doesn't
really like to be pushed.
- No.
- No, so there could be repercussions.
- Like what?
- Yeah, like, uh...
I don't know, just like...
Like if, uh, I've fucked it.
- You've fucked it?
- (PUTS BRACELET DOWN)
Right.
- (SNORTS)
- (GULPS)
I used to be a maniac.
A beast, but... It's a different
situation for me now.
Right. (LAUGHS)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
- You should hear yourself.
- Screw you.
- Yeah.
- Okay?
- (SNORTS)
- But there are levels.
Sure. No, it's true. Yeah,
I mean, I was basically
hanging by a fucking thread.
I'm coming through, you know?
- Like, I'm getting it together.
- Mm-hmm.
(SNIFFS) Yeah, me too.
- I know how that sounds, but...
- (LAUGHS)
... it's true.
(LAUGHS)
I can't even...
TABITHA: Those stars were amazing.
Can't even brush my fucking teeth now.
Such a fun weekend you brought me on.
Well. Am I stupid? Am I a
fucking idiot? Am I stupid?
- Ro?
- Yeah.
- I... I have a meeting on Monday.
- Uh-huh.
You know? And so I'd just,
like... I really wanna
deal with all your
neuroses and talk about it
and everything, but if you're
gonna get kind of crazy...
- Mm-hmm.
- ... I might just see if Naomi
would let me, you
know, crash in her bed.
- All right. Let's fuck.
- Yeah, totally.
We do the sex so well,
so, that's a great idea.
All right, come on. Come here,
you hot fucking piece of shit.
- (LAUGHING) Okay, okay, easy!
- (MOANS)
- Easy there, wolfman.
- Sorry.
- TABITHA: (LAUGHING) Oh, Jesus!
- ROMAN: That was awesome.
- I'm so fucking good at this.
- TABITHA: Christ!
- Oh!
- ROMAN: Sorry.
- It just was like...
- I know.
... really squeezing
hard with your finger.
- It was really sexy.
- (LAUGHS)
- Oh, how I just took you.
That was great. Um, do you...
Do you wanna, though? Can we...
Do you wanna?
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Do I want to... make love with me?
No. Wow. (GRUNTS)
Hey, hey. I'm not, uh...
I'm not uninterested in solving you.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm. Yes.
Do you think there's a
way that we can, like...
make it kinda like wrong?
(NAOMI LAUGHING)
(KENDALL SCREAMS)
(NAOMI SQUEALS)
NAOMI: Chopper ahoy.
- Oh, shit! (LAUGHS)
- (KENDALL GRUNTS)
Show me what you got!
- (SIGHS)
- (KENDALL GROANS)
- Okay.
- Mm!
Altimeter is go. Wiggle...
Wiggle stick, twisty stick is go.
- The throttle...
- NAOMI: Oh!
Turbo throttles. We gotta put these on.
- Spinny-spinny, chicken Dinny!
- (NAOMI LAUGHS)
NAOMI: You don't know what you're doing!
- Holy fuck!
- (GASPS)
- KENDALL: Uh...
- NAOMI: Wait.
- (KENDALL LAUGHS)
- No.
- (MUTTERING)
- NAOMI: No, no! Abort!
Turn it off, turn it off,
turn it off, turn it off.
We're good. I'm good.
We're okay. We're okay.
Yeah.
(LAUGHTER)
- We're good. That's good.
- (LAUGHS)
There's just a slight technical issue
with what I like to call the spriller.
- The spinner?
- The spinner.
You're such a little
nothing, aren't you?
Uh-huh. Maybe.
Uh... I don't... I'm just...
I'm just gonna put the light on.
ROMAN: Oh, don't... Okay, I wish
you didn't do that. That's...
I know, I just... I'm a
person who needs, like...
- Tabs, you're meant to be dead.
- ... visual stimulation
- to get into it, so...
- I know, I get that, but I...
- That will help us, I promise you.
- What about my needs? But don't...
Sure. I thought we could
just, like, try. You could just
- keep your eyes closed...
- Yeah, but you shouldn't be
turned on, because
dead women aren't wet.
- Um...
- Right, okay, um...
- Kinda ruining the realism.
- So... Let me just...
- Ow.
- Okay, okay.
You want it to seem like I'm dead,
- and you're raping me?
- I don't want to get into
a semantic arg... Oh, my God, no.
It's just gonna be a little less
like, "Sex, yay!"
Yeah, I... I...
Mm, I think maybe the morgue
is closing for the night.
Okay. It's just, I'm... I'm
just saying, if we, like,
politely agree on a wrong
thing, then it's no longer wrong.
I mean, I'm... That's just
like basic boner arithmetic.
I just... Yeah, no,
thank you for that lesson,
Professor Can't-Fuck. I'm,
uh... I'm gonna go in here,
and, you know, if you
hear my electric toothbrush
for a little too long, it's
because I'm masturbating, so...
Okay. Thank you.
NAOMI: When I had my, um, big...
My... biggest crackup...
My mom died.
And I couldn't get from
South Africa to this,
and you people and your fucking tabloids
just, like, all the time
pushing it and selling it,
until I put a cherry
on top and... (LAUGHS)
... I... wrapped my fucking
Audi around a highway divider.
So, yeah. Fuck you. Fuck your people,
and fuck your peace pipe.
You know what the
funny thing is, though?
That my wrist will never fully heal?
Or there's photos of me
caked in blood with my femur
- poking out?
- We all have something, right?
This deal isn't gonna change all that.
- I mean, all I would say is...
- Oh, you've got it all sorted.
Don't block your own escape.
Just imagine getting
out from under all this.
Right? You can take the money...
and you can just get the fuck out.
And then what?
Then, you're free.
Psst!
- Hi.
- Good God.
I was hoping we could touch
base about my entire future
being Hindenburged.
(SIGHS) Oh, the Romanity.
Come in or fuck off. This is loitering.
You know, I'm not available
24 hours a day like an ATM.
- Did you know about Shiv?
- No.
I mean, I didn't know-know, but...
Anybody who wasn't a fucking
moron would've figured it out.
Yeah, got it. Do you have any booze.
Here you go.
ROMAN: Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Thanks. If you have any, uh... Mm.
Suggestions for what I should
do for the rest of my life,
I'm all ears.
Well, I'm getting great reports
from the training program.
No shit! Amazing! Yes!
Fuck yeah! Training program!
Mm! Maybe one day, I can
be in charge of making
the rolly-coaster go...
(IMITATES ROCKET BLAST)
Alright, drink up because,
you know, it's bedtime.
- Let's go.
- Okay. Mm!
Unless you wanna schedule one
of our special conference calls
for, say, right now?
- Excuse me?
- Hi.
Wait, is that why you're here?
Mm-mm. No. I don't know.
Maybe. I don't know. No.
Jesus Christ.
Roman, this is unacceptable.
This is completely inappropriate.
- Yeah?
- What would your family say
if they knew you were here?
Oh, well, my family jimmy-fuck-corn,
- and I don't care.
- Yeah, but you do care.
- No.
- Yeah, I know you do.
And they would be ashamed
of you, and rightly so.
Okay, I'm very sorry,
Gerri how are you...
No, you don't get to speak.
You have always been a disappointment,
but this is just... You
have gone beyond the pale.
- I have?
- Oh, yeah.
You know what you are?
What am I?
You're a sick fuck. You're
a sick fucking animal.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, don't look at me.
Get in that bathroom. Now!
Go on.
And you will stay in there
until you have done
something with yourself.
You have a problem, Roman.
A revolting problem in your head.
This is why you'll never
be anything but a disgrace,
a rotten little nothing.
Jesus Christ, you are
- a classic fuckup, Roman.
- (ROMAN PANTING)
GERRI: What are we gonna do about you?
What if they could see you now?
- Oh, my God.
- (ROMAN MOANS)
So did anybody... Uh, anybody get
into any fun last night, or... ?
- Um...
- Fun?
I jerked off in Gerri's
bathroom last night.
- TABITHA: Hmm.
- Yeah.
- So classy of you.
- KENDALL: Morning.
It's okay. Don't worry about
it. It was actually her idea.
Think it really got the
old gal's juices flowing.
Even as a joke, that is
a stomach-turning thought.
(TABITHA LAUGHS)
NAN: ... about the family
dynamic of, I think he
wants to be successor.
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Con. I was just getting a headcount.
Did it blow up with Maxim?
A little. But then we cracked
open a bottle of port... (LAUGHS)
- and, uh, I, um... I'm not sure.
- (LAUGHS) What happened?
Uh... I got tipsy and I offered
him the State Department?
- Good?
- Yeah.
Good.
So, the family had a closed-door
meeting this morning.
- Uh-huh. Bad or good?
- I'm sorry, but, uh...
I'm blind on this one
too. You know, I...
I thought you'd have more time,
and I thought I could get in
and waggle the old screwdriver,
but, uh, she doesn't always
listen to me.
- So?
- But Nan would like to meet
you, Marcia, Gerri, Shiv,
Kendall after breakfast.
Relax. It's only life or death.
Please, take a seat. (CLEARS THROAT)
Is Marcia coming?
LOGAN: Uh, she's gone for a walk.
She is a credit. A lot
of men in your station,
they go for, uh, a certain... type.
Anyway, we all managed
to get through an evening
pleasantly enough. That's
not why we're here, is it?
No, it's not.
NAN: I have no illusions
about who Logan Roy is.
Who his children are. I'm not an idiot.
Well, something has to be
done. Eight straight quarters
of losses is a hard truth,
and we can't do good news
- without deep pockets.
- Uh-huh.
Call me a romantic, but I happen
to believe that the presence
of Pierce news cameras was
what stopped certain East German
border guards from opening fire in 1989.
We helped take down that wall.
Yes.
Commendable.
You may not believe that, but I do.
Now, here we are.
On the one hand, I do
not like you very much.
And I do not like your politics.
On the other hand, I had
a conversation this morning
with my cousin Naomi, and
she believes that a sale
is the only way to ensure
that Pierce Media can flourish.
And that may be where we are.
Rhea, what do you think?
I think... I think we're worth more.
We have made a very generous offer
in terms of market valuations.
- RHEA: Nevertheless.
- I don't like to be squeezed.
- I thought we had a number.
- Uh-huh.
Yeah. And, uh, I mean...
Hmm.
I could go to 25.
But it would have to be fast.
Then, in that case...
with a certain heaviness
of heart, if I honestly had
to say, from the family's
point of view...
yes.
(NAN CLEARS THROAT)
Very well. If we can clear
up our ethical concerns,
I think we can talk.
We would like to
retain some board seats,
and get ironclad editorial
protections in place.
I think that could be hammered out.
- NAN: Also.
- Also.
I think we would also
like to have a conversation
about management.
- LOGAN: Uh-huh.
- I won't have that man
overseeing our news. I'm
sorry. It's just not tenable.
That won't be a problem.
NAN: More important, we would
like you to publicly announce
a successor.
LOGAN: Mm-hmm.
And we would like the
person you publicly announce
to be Siobhan Roy.
LOGAN: Well...
that's not quite how I do things.
Well, it will have to
be, or there's no deal.
We want to announce the sale
and Shiv at the same time,
because, frankly, she may be
one of you, but she's young,
she's a woman, and her politics
fit better with the core values
of our family business. So...
that's the offer.
Well, to be fair, you
don't have an offer.
I have an offer.
And if I announce my daughter,
my daughter will be
announced on my time.
NAN: Okay. Let me explain something.
- Oh, please.
- You can't put a value
on what we do.
Funny. I have put a
value on what you do.
Well, if you won't budge, then
I'm afraid we have no deal.
Then we're done.
Uh...
Would you like to hear
my favorite passage from Shakespeare?
Take the fucking money.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
What a weird family.
(LOGAN SIGHS)
(INHALES)
So, you wanna talk about it?
- You wanna say something, fine.
- Uh... What happened?
LOGAN: Uh... (MURMURS)
Hmm. (GRUNTS)
- (YELLS)
- SHIV: Jesus Christ, Dad!
- What?
- It's dangerous!
- We good?
- Drive your fucking whirly-bird!
Yeah? Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Uh-huh. (SCOFFS)
That's god-damn fucking right!
- Should we go?
- SHIV: Yeah. He won't talk.
Let's have one more and
we'll get out of here.
Hey, Richard. Ah! Oh, my God!
You guys! You g... You did it!
That... Yeah, congratulations!
- ALL: Hey.
- Hey.
- Yeah!
- MARCIA: Hello, Greg.
Um, actually going by
Gregory, now, but, uh... yeah.
No matter. (CHUCKLES)
Uh, thank you, Richard.
- Wow. How are you, Marcia?
- Good, thanks.
Good. And how... How was it?
How wa... Was it awesome, or... ?
Uh... Yeah, it was eventful.
KENDALL: Yeah, it was good. It was good.
Nice of you to come by, man.
GREG: No worries. This
is huge for us! Um...
And this, like, saves us,
maybe, from the takeover.
- LOGAN: Greg!
- Hey! Gregory!
Have a drink, have a drink,
you beautiful Ichabod Crane!
- Fuck you! (LAUGHS)
- Yeah! (LAUGHS) Oh, wow.
Well, I j... I gotta
say, well done. You won.
Yeah. Yeah. Money wins.
- Here's to us.
- ALL: To us.
- KENDALL: To us.
- TABITHA: To us.
Hey, nice vest, Wamsgans.
It's so puffy.
What's it stuffed with,
your hopes and dreams?
SHIV ROY: There's a
potential crisis coming.
There's a journalist
looking into cruises,
and there's a big piece coming.
Let's finish the job before this breaks.
How long do we have,
hours, maybe minutes?
LOGAN: Can you persuade her
to ink it here tomorrow?
RHEA JARRELL: If Nan gets
cold feet and you can't buy us,
your dad could lose control.