Now, I know this is a car show,
but please bear with us, because
I want to talk about this.
It's one of those watches that
are worn by people who play golf
and do business.
And they're always banging on about
these pins, that you can see here.
Yeah. They say that if
they pull those pins out,
the watch will send
their precise position
to a team of professionals,
who will come and rescue them.
So, if they're out
climbing a mountain,
or rowing across an ocean...
Which they aren't, because they're
playing golf and doing business.
No, but if they were doing those
things and something went wrong,
then, thanks to their
watch, they'd be OK.
Ah, but would they?
To find out, the producers
decided that one of us
should be dumped somewhere with minimal
kit, with virtually no food,
somewhere very, very remote,
to see if the system works.
Well...
.. that's it.
I am now marooned here...
.. wherever the hell "here" is.
Bloody hell...
My only hope now is my watch, so...
.. it's time.
I undo this...
.. there...
.. and then, pull that bit out...
.. and that's it, done.
Pulling those pins activates
a distress signal
that's picked up by a LEOSAR
low Earth polar orbit satellite,
which then forwards
my exact coordinates
to a central command centre.
The team here then scramble
the nearest highly-trained
search and rescue unit,
who arrive at my location
within hours.
Sadly, however,
today, the scramble command
has not been sent
to a highly-trained search
and rescue unit.
- .. Running on petrol.
- It's a brilliant idea.
- I'm not sure the Ferrari does that.
- DEVICE BEEPS
I think it does, but I think they're
just being honest about it,
because they're recognising that
it's a means of improving
the efficiency...
Is that your bag ringing?
Oh, I think this is the signal
from our esteemed colleague,
- Richard Hammond.
- Is it? Where is he?
- Wait a minute.
He would appear to be in... Africa.
- Is it?
- Let's have a look.
No, I'll think you'll
find that is... Canada.
Specifically, the Rockies.
Crikey. Um...
Actually, that is quite serious.
We really do need to get
on with this, James, so...
Excuse me?
Could we see the pudding menu?
Right...
That bit suspends off this bit...
- That watch transmits for 24 hours...
- WATCH BEEPS
.. and then, that's it.
Right, so, this is the mountain,
there's my tent.
Mountain, trees, hills,
this is all we are.
There's a cameraman,
a sound recordist
and a bloke from the office --
and he's just a media luvvie.
I know you think there's a five-star
hotel just down there,
but there's not.
Nothing else. There's no
survival experts here.
Fact of the matter is,
I'm completely stuck
until Yogi the Bore
and Boo-Boo get here.
Knowing we were his only hope,
we had some important
decisions to make.
"Raunchy apple fritters" sounds quite
interesting. Pancake with cheese...
James? James, James, James...
You know in the colonies --
Australia, South Africa,
America, Canada and so on?
- Everybody loves pick-up trucks, yes?
- Yes.
Well, why don't we get a pick-up
truck to go and rescue Hammond in?
Because pick-up trucks generally
only have two seats
and there would be three of
us, when we've rescued him.
Well, we get two pick-up trucks
-- one for you, one for me.
It would A, increase our
chances of finding him,
and B, there'd be a seat
to get him back in.
- But...
- In Thunderbirds...
Inevitably, One and Two kind of
went first, didn't they? Always?
Yeah.
Alan and... No, not Alan.
Who drove Thunderbird One?
- Scott.
- Virgil.
- No, Virgil was Two.
- Was he Two?
Scott was One,
Virgil was Two, Alan was
Three, Gordon was Four...
Gordon!
In Canada, the temperature
was a bitter minus ten,
so I urgently needed some warmth.
What would have been wrong
with giving me a lighter?
Can't get my fire lit. Cold beans.
They're a bit frozen in the middle.
'Having finished our lunch...'
I'm not sure about the red, you know?
'We went to book some
flights to Vancouver.'
OK, you've actually just missed
the last flight out today.
- Have we?
- Yeah.
- Oh, what a rotten bit of luck.
Shouldn't we get another drink?
There's a Delta one that leads
at ten o'clock tomorrow morning.
I don't like Delta's seat upholstery.
Would you go from Manchester?
Manchester? No, you
know, this is the BBC.
I think it would be idiotic
to go to Manchester.
- I mean, that would be just stupid.
- There's Lufthansa...
Er, stewardesses wear trousers.
- There's one from Gatwick,
which goes via Calgary...
- Gatwick?
- He doesn't like Gatwick.
- I hate Gatwick.
WOLF HOWLS
Out there, somewhere...
.. there are bears...
.. as many as 180,000 black bears.
I can't remember what it was
-- about 15,000 grizzlies?
Freezing.
In the morning, I was cold and
exhausted from lack of sleep --
but most of all, I was anxious.
- Any minute now.
- WATCH BEEPS
Any minute.
I mean, they've had 24 hours.
I mean, 24 hours?
You can get anywhere in the
world in 24 hours, surely?
Where the hell are they?
JET ENGINES ROAR
- I can't remember...
- James?
- We've stopped beeping.
- Well, yeah. It would.
- Why would it?
Cos the watch thing only transmits
the distress signal for 24 hours.
Then the battery runs out.
- Seriously?
- Well, yeah. It's only...
- Well, did you make a note of where he was?
- No, I didn't.
You've got the thing.
Well, I remember he was...
He was on something called...
I think it was "Wolf Mountain"
and you go up "Bear Pass".
Sounds GRIZZLY.
LAUGHTER
That was a good joke.
Do you know, actually, the biggest
problem is not bears and wolves...
- Cougars. Loads of cougars.
- Well, that's all right, then.
No, not that sort of cougar.
[JEREMY GROWLS] That sort of cougar.
Oh, you mean like a big cat thing?
As I couldn't move from the spot
where the watch had transmitted
the distress signal,
I was hard at work trying to make
my life here more comfortable.
I want somewhere to sit.
I can't sit on the snow,
so I'm building a shelter.
Spark, you [BLEEP!]
There we go.
We have fire.
And with my supplies dwindling,
I also needed to think about food.
Animals for food...
.. guinea pigs.
All animals can be a
source of nourishment.
A few, including worms and insects,
can be collected with little skill.
I'm bored, I'm cold, I'm unhappy,
I'm hungry, I'm scared...
Agh!
And I don't want to be wearing
a hat, just for a minute!
Ah!
To alleviate the boredom
and stave off the cold,
I tried to make some SAS-style
pine needle tea.
Agh!
Ow, ow!
Ow!
Where are they?! Just where?
'Unfortunately, we were a little
bit delayed at Vancouver airport.'
Yes, of course.
'But eventually, we made
it to the car park,
'where our pick-up truck rescue
vehicles were waiting.'
MUSIC: The Launch by Boston
- James?
- Yeah?
That's not a light, that's
a collapsed sun, isn't it?
Never mind that, look --
mine actually comes up to my nipples.
I didn't realise it was... Do you
know what the other thing is?
If I actually find Richard Hammond,
I'm not going to see him, and I?
I'll just run straight over him.
Have you noticed something
else about mine?
This entire vehicle...
is a transportation device
for its own spare wheel, look!
That's all the back is for!
- That's really stupid.
Look at the size of it!
- Look at it!
Anyway, we've got
everything we need here.
I've got a big, warm coat,
I've got a massive car,
a rough idea of where
Richard Hammond is...
Yeah, so let's go...
into Vancouver, get a hotel,
good night's rest,
get rid of this jet lag.
ENGINE REVS
It's not funny. I don't know...
They've got to get here tomorrow...
morning -- early.
WOLF HOWLS
Now, my guest tonight was
Jordan Belfort's wife
in The Wolf Of Wall Street,
one of my favourite films
of the modern age.
She's now in a new film and she's
brought along her co-star,
so please welcome Margot Robbie
and a man called Will Smith!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Oh, heavens above!
Look what we've got for you!
Yeah, we got you as well.
Good to see you, good to see you.
Good to see you both.
I'll go round here.
- Thanks for having us.
- And relax.
Have a seat.
- This is fantastic!
- Isn't this fantastic?
- This is great.
I was almost going to begin by
apologising for the trailers.
- The trailers? Oh, those trailers, yeah.
- They're really nice.
- Will set his bar very high
with trailers though, so...
- Really?
Yeah, his trailer is pimp.
Yeah, I'm very serious
about the trailer.
The trailer, it has to be...
You've got to hook it up, you've
got to have a stereo system...
Yours had mirrors on the roof.
LAUGHTER
MOUTHS: No, it didn't.
I'm not insinuating anything,
I'm just saying...
That's going to get in trouble.
That's going to get into trouble.
Already in trouble,
where my mind's gone.
- Really, not that long ago,
you were in Neighbours.
- Yeah.
What interests me about Neighbours,
which is an Aussie TV show...
- I know what Neighbours is, man!
- Don't pretend you know!
I know what Neighbours is...
Two days ago, they asked him
what show I did in Australia --
a very popular show -- and you
said it started with "C"...
- I couldn't remember the name...
- There's no "C" in it.
I just can't see Will Smith
finishing a day at work going,
"Do you know, I think
I'll watch Neighbours."
- "6.30, my show's on!"
- Russell Crowe started in that, didn't he?
- Guy Pearce was another
one, Kylie's another one...
- Yeah, yeah.
And I always wondered, do
you know Coronation Street?
- Because that's produced literally...
- Yeah, I know all those shows, man!
- You don't. And...
- I've got the DVDs and everything!
- It's just unbelievable.
- I have all this, the... the...
Coronation Street and
Neighbours and all those.
EastEnders, yeah.
- Now, you're over here,
obviously, to promote a film.
- Yes.
It's called Focus, but it isn't
about the small Ford hatchback...
which disappointed
some people in here.
It's a love story between you
two, which is rather sweet.
- Yeah.
- It's interesting, it's...
My character plays a conman,
a master thief
and part of being a master
thief is, he's a liar.
And he meets Margot's
character, Jess,
and falls madly in love
and realises quickly that lying and
loving don't go together too well.
- They go together often...
- LAUGHTER
.. but they don't go together well.
- I believe we have a clip,
which we're going to show now.
- Really? OK.
MUSIC: It's A Man's, Man's,
Man's World by James Brown
- Are you working an angle?
- I wouldn't trust him, if I were you.
But I should trust you?
- You've got a problem.
- I am going to kill you.
Kill me later.
- You lost everyone's money -- my money!
- Hey!
- Wow.
- This is your mess.
- I think you're losing it.
- Why'd you come up here?
- Professional curiosity.
And I like boobs. I figured
it was a win-win.
CRASH
At the end of the day,
this is a game of focus.
APPLAUSE
Did you notice when
I had my shirt off?
You noticed, didn't you?
Did you see that shot?
Yes, that's what everyone is
aware of in that trailer...
- I just want to know if you saw the shot!
- Margo had her trousers off.
- Oh, yes. You saw that(!)
- Slightly more distracting...
I get that, I get that.
And I've seen you with no
shirt on a million times,
but I've never seen... Well, I have
seen Margot with no trousers on.
LAUGHTER
I've never seen...
- This just got awkward.
- It did.
Now, one of the things that
make it even more awkward is,
you filmed quite a lot of
the movie in Argentina...
Yes, yeah.
LAUGHTER
How did that go for you?
For me? It was good,
it was good, man.
Argentina is fantastic.
- Is it(?)
- LAUGHTER
- What's wrong with Argentina?
- What's wrong with Argentina? What happened?
Every [BLEEP] thing!
LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE
- No, but it is... I enjoyed
it and best of luck with it.
- Thank you.
- When does it open?
- 27th.
Is it the 27th here?
- Yes!
- Yeah.
- OK, yes.
Now, we've got to get on to cars,
- cos you grew up on a farm in Australia...
- Mm.
.. so you, presumably, have
been driving since you were 0,
- because it's such a vast area.
- Yeah, it's huge.
In our family, the rule was, you
could drive as soon as you could...
physically reach the pedals.
You could have the car on your own
when you reached double digits.
- So, when you were ten,
you were allowed to...
- Wow.
All the children at home are going...
And I remember being nine years
old and arguing with the parents,
being like, "Guys, this is
absurd. I'm not, like..."
And they're like, "No, you're nine.
You have to wait another year."
I was like, "This is... I can't
believe this! This is ridiculous."
- Have you been out to the outback?
- No, no, no.
I feel like you'd fit
right in. You got it.
See, it's a racial thing.
You went racial.
- Yeah, that's what it's about(!)
- LAUGHTER
So, what was your first car?
It was a candy apple red IROC-Z --
a Camaro.
Apparently, you don't
have those here.
No, we don't, no. We have...
What's the word? Taste.
LAUGHTER
I was thinking, maybe this
indicates you don't know
anything about cars -- then I started
to look in some of the lyrics.
- Are you familiar with the
lyrics of the early songs?
- Oh, jeez.
- I wasn't born.
- In a song called Gettin' Jiggy Wit It...
- Yes.
- I've heard of that. Yeah, I know that one.
I don't recognise that one.
He's got "850iS..."
"850iS if you need a lift."
"Who's the kid in the drop?"
"Who else? Will Smith."
They're all there. Now, "drop"
I presume means "drop top"...
Drop top, yes.
- They never did a drop top 850.
- They...
LAUGHTER
- It's a small...
- APPLAUSE
See, now here...
He thinks he knows everything,
he thinks he knows everything.
In the United States, we do a thing
where we customise our cars(!)
LAUGHTER
- Can I just give you another one?
- This is brilliant.
- Just Cruisin'.
"The Maestro."
- You know the next bit?
- Yes, yes.
- "Nice flow...
"Nice flow, hot like nitro.
- "Cool as...
- Cool as ice, though."
- It's a dichotomy.
- Do you know what a Maestro is?
- Oh, you've got one?
- There you go.
- LAUGHTER
Oh, my God!
It is so awkward for me
to hear you say my lyrics.
LAUGHTER
- I'll bet.
- It's making my eyes water!
We've done enough of this now.
We want to get on to your laps.
- OK, yeah.
- How did you enjoy it out there?
- It was really fun.
- It was really nerve-racking,
but it was really fun.
- Was it?
- Yeah.
It was fantastic. I've never...
- In the United States, the
stick is on the other side.
- Yeah.
So, having to drive and do it
with the other hand, it was...
That's an advantage for you, of course --
because you're used to driving like this.
- Which is why he's obviously
mentioning it right now.
- Yeah, he's already starting...
He's like, "In case he
beats me on the laps,
- "it's the whole stick-side thing..."
- In case her time was better.
- OK.
Margot, you went first and...
Well, there was a bit of an off.
Crashed.
Who'd like to see Margot's lift?
I said specifically, "Let's not
let Will know that that happened."
LAUGHTER
- Let's have a look. Come
on, let's play the tape.
- Oh, good.
Oh, whoa -- it's Chicago.
It's understeer on Chicago.
MARGOT YELPS
- Ooh! Oh!
- It's Ian, it's Ian!
It's Ian the cameraman.
- Sorry!
- LAUGHTER
And he's dead.
APPLAUSE
- Margot, we have a little...
- I am sorry about that.
Relax, we've got a little
present for you.
- It's the landing light unit.
- LAUGHTER
You can take that home, as a souvenir
of your trip to Top Gear.
I'm so sorry!
- Right. Now, we've got both your
laps to have a look at, so...
- OK.
- .. ladies first.
- Ladies first, yeah.
- Let's have a look at your lap.
This is going to end in a fist fight.
- Right, here we go.
- ENGINE REVS
BRAKES SCREECH
Good, clean, aggressive start.
Up to third...
Let's have a look at this.
Good dab of the breaks.
It feels so much faster in the clip.
Everybody says it, but the
slower you look, weirdly...
Actually, I don't know. There's
a lot of understeer there.
That's ballsy.
Oh, God!
Here we go, we're going to make
it without running over Ian...
Oh, waving to Ian! There's a
little wave there, that's nice.
That was a "Sorry, Ian".
Don't brake, don't
brake, don't brake...
"Don't brake, don't brake!"
BRAKES SCREECH
- You do look like you're
concentrating in there.
- Yeah.
Trying not to hit anyone this time.
This is good. I'm liking
the look of this.
MARGOT SIGHS
- Right, coming up to the fastest bit.
- Foot down, foot down, foot down.
Confidence, that was. That
was the look of confidence.
- Get through the tyres, yes.
- Whoo!
- That does look quick, though.
- That was the fun run. I liked that.
- Second to last corner.
- This is what normally catches people out.
- Yeah, that's the one.
Through there easily,
through Gambon...
More understeer! A lot of understeer
and across the line. There we are.
APPLAUSE
And now...
- That was pretty... That was strong.
- It is strong, Mr Will Smith.
- Yeah, nah, but everything
was on the left for me...
- Yeah, yeah(!)
- Any more?
- I had back surgery, like three days ago.
LAUGHTER
Who'd like to see the lap with the
poor man with the back surgery?
CHEERING
Let's have a look. Here we go.
- BRAKES SCREECH
- Whoa, that was some revs!
- Yup.
- Whoo!
- All right, this is the one.
- Did you do a few practices?
Yeah, I did a few practice laps.
That's a hard bit of braking
mid-corner, there.
I'll tell you what, though --
that car bullied GM's finest.
Powering through, feeling good.
There we go. This is the spiritual
successor of the IROC-Z....
I'm on the wall now. They're
putting me on the wall.
My name, with all of the
fastest times on this track.
That is a confident man right there.
It's actually lovely conditions
for fast times, this.
Keeping it in the lines nicely.
Yes, just like watching Daniel
Ricciardo all over again.
This is the one that
makes my children proud.
Keeping in there -- no
braking, flat-out, yeah?
- No braking, flat-out.
- Good man.
Yeah, that's looking very tidy.
Second to last corner,
you have any problems?
No, that is neat. Very neat
-- and through Gambon...
Still on all four wheels,
unlike some people --
- and there we are, across the line!
- APPLAUSE
- That was nice.
- So much fun.
Well done, you two.
Where do you think you've
come on the board?
Uh...
I'd be really psyched if I get
on the board, to be honest.
You can't not be on it,
because trust me --
Jack Whitehall, Ed Sheeran...
So, there's space down there
for me? OK. I want 1.52.
1.52? And Will?
Uh... Well, I want, like, 1.22...
LAUGHTER
You asked what think I did.
I think I might be in the 1.50 zone,
right in there.
- Somewhere with the Hugh
Bonneville, Tom Huddleston...
- I felt like I...
These were wet times. Let's have
a look, shall we? Let's have a look.
- I've got the times here.
- OK.
- I'm going to do you first, Will.
- OK. Oh, jeez.
- This is really exciting.
- Will Smith...
- This is very exciting.
- You did a 1...
- That's a good start.
- .. 40...
- Ooh.
.. 7... Whoa.
- .. 2. OK, yeah.
- And that isn't bad at all.
APPLAUSE
That puts you...
- Wow. OK, yeah.
- That's really great.
- We like that.
- That is not bad at all.
And now, we must get
on to your co-star.
- OK.
- Oh...
If you beat me, this is
your last day on the tour.
LAUGHTER
I will never work again after this.
It's Leo, Will Smith and then, TV.
LAUGHTER
Margot...
1... Oh, good.
- .. 40...
- Ooh!
- AUDIENCE GASPS
- What?!
- She'd better not.
LAUGHTER
- .. 7...
- Oh!
- AUDIENCE GASPS
She'd better not, she'd better not...
- .. 1!
- Oh!
- CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
I'm not making it up!
I'm sorry!
[BLEEP!]
This was a bad idea.
It's like the Academy Awards,
where you've got to clap
for the other person.
- I don't know what to say now.
- I actually can't believe that.
- Both of you have done amazing times.
- Oh, my God!
There was a tenth in it,
neither of you have got anything
to be ashamed about.
Oh, no -- one of us has something
to be ashamed about!
LAUGHTER
- I was trying to end on a really high note...
- No, no...
.. coming up with some nice things...
But you're right.
Ladies and gentlemen, I
think you'll all agree,
this has been an absolute joy.
Will Smith and Margot Robbie!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Now, last year, McLaren
gave us the astonishing P1
and Porsche gave us the
equally fantastic 918,
but we've always known that there
is another hybrid supercar coming.
Well, it's not coming any more.
It's here, it's the one you've
all been waiting for
and I have been driving it.
The Ferrari "The Ferrari"!
McLaren and Porsche may believe
they've created good-looking
cars in the P1 and the 918...
.. but I think they need to get
their pencil cases out again,
because this is what a
supercar should look like.
And this is what a supercar
should sound like.
ENGINE THRUMS AND REVS
No miserable V8s or puny
little turbochargers --
that is Ferrari's greatest hit.
The sound of 12 cylinders
properly arranged in a V.
Molto grazie!
And then, there's the price --
LaFerrari has the other
two licked there, as well.
The Porsche 918 -- £646,000.
The McLaren P1 -- £866,000.
The LaFerrari...
£1,000,000!
That's a proper price
-- no mucking about!
'And there's more.'
Pinky and Perky have
been at great pains
to explain just how clever the
McLaren and the Porsche are.
Well, this is also very clever.
'It's built from not one, but four
different types of carbon fibre
'to keep it as light as possible.
'In fact, it's lighter than
the Porsche or the McLaren.
'The driver's seat is fixed
'and instead it's the wheel
and pedals that move.
'This means you don't
need a seat mechanism,
'which means the driver can sit
lower, the roof can be lower
'and that drops the
centre of gravity...
'.. to the benefit of cornering.
'Then we come to the engine.'
Like the McLaren and the Porsche,
LaFerrari is a hybrid.
It has a petrol engine AND an electric
motor to drive the wheels.
But, whereas the other two
can be driven on electric power
alone like a Toyota Prius,
the Ferrari can't because,
Ferrari say, "We are not
interested in electric cars."
'Instead, the battery and
electric motor combination
'works a bit like the kinetic energy
recovery system in an F1 car.
'In very simple terms,
'it captures energy that's
normally wasted --
'during braking, for example -'
'and keeps it for when you need it.'
The electric motor,
the petrol engine --
they're all working together
all of the time.
You cannot separate them.
This is simply a 950
horsepower supercar.
'But, despite the racing technology,
'you don't find yourself in a world
of austere track car misery.'
You've got the sat-nav,
the air conditioning.
It's perfectly comfortable.
Actually, it's very civilised.
'However, this is also
supposed to be the fastest
'and most exciting road
car Ferrari has ever made.
'And to find out how exciting,
we must come here...
'.. Ferrari's Fiorano test track.
'To prancing horse fans,
this is the sacred tarmac
'where the company's greatest
F1 cars were born.
'But, when I rolled up, sacred wasn't
the word that came to mind.'
THUNDER RUMBLES
Oh, cock!
'After two hours of dithering
on the start line...'
- WHIRRING
- Pedals -- a little bit further away.
No, that's too far away. Hang on.
'.. the track was finally dry
enough for me to have a go.'
Red, red, red...
God's holy trousers!
Strewth, I'm already
at the first bend.
Lots of brakes.
That, ladies and gentlemen,
is 950 horsepower for you.
And while we're at it,
950 horsepower is a slam dunk
Top Trump over the other two.
And so is the top speed -- 218mph.
'But it's not just the amount of
horsepower that's impressive --
'it's the way it's served up.'
Even if you're a bit
clumsy or a bit timid,
as I am being on this one, you've
still got that enormous grunt.
It just hits you like
a runaway train.
That's the KERS system working.
That's exactly what it's for.
'On top of that, Ferrari has
remembered that not everyone
'who'll drive this car will be
called Sebastian or Vettel.'
Because LaFerrari will go quite
a lot faster than you can think,
Ferrari do quite a lot of thinking
for you. It has, for example,
a very sophisticated
traction control system
based on Formula 1 tech.
And you can leave it turned on.
Why not? It stops you crashing.
'LaFerrari also bristles
with active aerodynamics.
'That's not new on a supercar,
'but this system is controlled
by 21 computers, which means,
'according to the Ferrari eggheads,
'even I should be able to take
Fiorano's notorious turn seven...
'flat out.'
Active aerodynamics, here we go!
Don't bottle it, don't bottle it!
Ho-ho-ho!
It works! Look at that!
The faster you go,
the better it works!
I mean, like Jennifer's McLaren,
it is pure rear-wheel drive,
and that is quite intimidating,
but it's not a widow maker.
Oh, my God!
Whoa, yes!
Wahey! Sorry.
Let's just slow this down a bit.
Richard Hammond, he
says the Porsche 918,
that's the one that takes the
hybrid supercar the furthest,
it's the most responsible,
if you like.
Jeremy likes the P1 because
he says it takes an idea
that was essentially
an environmental one
and uses it to make the
supercar more dramatic.
'In this respect, the Ferrari
is more like the McLaren.'
Except for two things --
LaFerrari looks better...
.. and I reckon it IS better.
This is the greatest
car in the world!
Now, tonight, Jeremy and I are using
two huge American pick-up trucks
to rescue Richard Hammond,
who's been abandoned
- LAUGHTER
- on a freezing cold mountain top
in the Canadian Rockies.
We pick up the action after
we'd had a good night's rest
in a downtown Vancouver hotel.
'We set off before dawn, not knowing
exactly where Hammond was,
'but we did know he was
at least 400 miles away,
'so we had plenty of time to
get to know our vehicles.'
I am driving a Ford
F-150 pick-up truck,
which is by miles the
best-selling vehicle in America.
Ford sells one of these
things every 35 seconds
and that's only in America, remember.
35 seconds!
If you were to park every
F-150 that's ever been made
since 1948 side by side
-- not end to end,
side by side -- the line would
stretch round the Equator...
twice!
'The reason it sells so well
is simple -- it's cheap.'
You can have an F-150 with an
automatic gearbox, cruise control,
air conditioning and
a 350 horsepower...
AMERICAN ACCENT: .. V8 motor
for the equivalent of £20,000.
That's what we pay in Europe
for a Vauxhall Astra diesel.
'By comparison, my pick-up
truck is a sales disaster.'
What I'm driving here,
viewers, the Silverado --
the Chevrolet Silverado -- is the
second-best-selling pick-up truck.
They only manage to shift
one of these every minute.
I'm amazed Chevrolet
are still in business.
'Meanwhile, very far away, my third
day on the mountain was beginning.'
I didn't sleep last night,
I was cold all night.
I'm going to have to
get more firewood.
The thought of that, swinging
that axe AGAIN...
It's probably a good diet, this.
You'll see it on This
Morning at some point.
"Well, what you need is to be
abandoned by two good friends.
"Well, when I say 'good
friends', I mean 'bastards'."
- Look!
- That's what I call a breakfast.
- Thank you very much.
- Yeah, that's perfect.
'After our winter-warming breakfast,
we were back on the road
'and delving once more
into our pick-up trucks.'
I'm going to be honest with you.
This is no ordinary F-150.
This is the top of the
range Raptor model,
which has been beefed up,
supercharged and intercooled
and then renamed VelociRaptor
by a company called Hennessey,
makers of the Venom,
one of the fastest road cars
the world has ever seen.
So, the 6.2 litre V8 I have under
the bonnet produces -- ahem --
623 horsepower.
That's 212 more than standard.
And that makes it quick.
Alarmingly quick!
ENGINE ROARS
Listen to THAT!
It's like a jet.
'While Jeremy was in a
supercharged rocket ship,
'I was riding a wave
of lowdown grunt.'
I have at my disposal a 6.6 litre
turbo-charged V8 diesel engine.
It develops 765 pound-feet of torque.
That's more than one of those
Supersports Bentley Continentals!
I also have the Z71 Off-Road Package,
which means I get a lot of underbody
strengthening, beefed-up dampers
and it has, as standard,
a sophisticated four-wheel
drive system.
I think, for International Rescue,
this is like Thunderbird 2.
It's the one that does all the
really serious, proper work.
'With 52 hours gone
'and International Rescue
nowhere in sight,
'I was resorting to extreme
measures to find food.'
This is the snare.
It just tightens like that.
I lay this on the rabbit
trail, which is here.
Foot -- caught, rabbit -- dinner.
There! Apparently, the way
you bait it is with pee.
VELCRO UNFASTENING
ZIP OPENS
Another layer... Two...
Four...
What if a bear comes now?
'Meanwhile, James and I, keen
to be ready for any emergency,
'had decided to buy vital
rescue equipment.'
- What's that bit there for?
- A can opener. A bottle opener.
- What...
- It's a bottle opener.
- It opens beer. Yes! We want them.
- That's worth having, isn't it?
- What is it?
- Scrapey-scrapey, brushy-brushy.
- We don't need a brush.
Well, OK, saw the brush off.
I can't buy just one end, can I?
No, no, see, there's just one end.
Yeah, but you might as
well have a brush as well.
No, you don't need a brush.
WOLF HOWLS
I haven't made these exactly
like the ones in the book
cos I once saw Ray
Mears make snowshoes
and they were more like this.
Ahhh! Cold!
REALLY COLD!
That's it -- that's where I peed.
No rabbit.
It's all rubbish! Nothing works!
Where the [BLEEP] are they?
MUSIC: More Than A Feeling by Boston
I have my seat heater
on. It's very nice.
I really am starting to deeply
like my VelociRaptor.
This reminds me -- and you're
going to think I'm mad,
but it's true -- it reminds me of
a 1992 supercharged Aston Martin.
They're very similar.
I used to LOVE that car.
This looks like rather
an attractive small town.
I wouldn't mind stopping for
something like a cappuccino.
'By mid-afternoon, there was still
no sign of Yogi and Boo-Boo,
'so I prepared myself for
a third night in the open.'
And if you want to write
to the BBC and say,
"This is some rare type of
tree and has to be preserved",
you can stick it up your arse.
Sick of the sight of this place.
I'm a television presenter from
Birmingham, not Bear [BLEEP] Grylls.
Despite our best efforts,
James and I were still more than 150
miles from our friend and colleague.
Night was falling, the
roads were getting worse
and there was another issue.
Sitrep -- James May does
not like driving in the snow
and has now reduced his
speed to about three.
To annoy him as much
as he was annoying me,
I decided to ignite my collapsed sun.
Right.
CLARKSON!
I have never, ever encountered
a light like that
- on the front of a car.
- Seriously, very funny,
but could you turn the big light off?
Only when you speed up.
Turn the [BLEEP] light off!
It was a long, horrible drive
but, mercifully, when we were
just ten miles from Hammond,
we found a lodge where
we could spend the night.
And, the next morning,
I came up with a plan.
Hammond is ten miles away
and 4,000 feet above us,
so we have a race,
and, if you get there first,
you don't have to rescue him.
Come on, that's an incentive.
No, you're right, it is, isn't it?
So, if you don't get there first,
you have to drive, what?
15 hours back to Vancouver
with Richard Hammond
in your pick-up truck.
Can you imagine driving 15 hours
back to Vancouver with him
either dead or bad-tempered?
Where the [BLEEP] are you?
I peed in a bottle in my tent
last night and it felt dirty!
Enough!
With a good breakfast
under our belts,
James and I were planning our routes.
So, Hammond is around there.
That's where the signal
came from from his watch,
so, if I go up what
I think is Wolf Pass,
the corpse of Richard Hammond
will be around here somewhere.
It's slightly longer, but it's
only a little bit longer,
but I'm avoiding that massive rise.
I'm going to go that way.
You ready, mate?
I've never been more ready.
Three, two, one -- begin!
This is an interesting
race, it really is,
because, although our pick-up
trucks appear to be the same...
.. but, actually, they're
not the same at all.
His is all about strength and torque
and this is all about
speed and power.
And, then, there's
our driving styles.
James's is very slow and
methodical and full of maths,
mine's more sort of...
ENGINE REVS
.. put your foot down
and hope for the best.
Traction control is on.
Thumbs outside the wheel. That's
the other off-road tip.
Absolutely gorgeous scenery.
Hammond will have been having
a lovely time looking at this.
It's like being at a spa.
[BLEEP.]
You are going on there.
In the Ford, I'd decided to
use one of God's highways.
Rivers, as we know, are level
unless they're waterfalls.
I just hope we don't
encounter one of those.
There's my camera. Yep. I
can now see what I'm doing.
Two miles completed.
No serious problems.
Jeez!
Yes. Good work.
I love my pick-up truck.
I really love it.
Both of us were now off
the beaten track
and full of steely determination.
Come on, Jeremy. You
need to get there first.
Thunderbird 1 is power sliding.
Oh, yes!
This is called wrestling
with the controls.
Whoa!
Oh!
♪ Silverado
♪ Why don't you come
to your senses? ♪
Temperatures and pressures
all in the green.
This is shouting and power
versus thought and torque.
Come on!
I've got some rooster tails now!
Oh!
Good news, Hammond, the VelociRaptor
works well in these conditions.
Where is he? Where is he?
Hello. Hello.
I'm James. Oh, I'm Jeremy.
Shall we be friends, James?
Yes, let's be best friends
for ever and ever.
Right, James, I must tell
you all about myself.
Actually, that's my favourite hobby
-- telling people how wonderful I am.
Oh, is it really, Jeremy?
That's funny,
because I actually am
brilliant... Are you?
Yes, I am but I'm very
modest. Are you?
Yes, that's what I drive
a yellow Ferrari. Do you?
I drive everything better
than everybody else.
Let's have another friend but let's
leave him to die on a mountaintop,
shall we? Oh, that would
be funny, wouldn't it?
Knowing that Hammond
would be on high ground,
I was now climbing hard.
God, I love this thing.
I really, properly do.
All day yesterday, this was
an Aston Martin V8 Vantage.
Now it's a Group B Audi Quattro.
On my route, I too was climbing.
Do your stuff, Z71 Pack.
You can actually feel
the wheels going,
"Is it this one? Is it that one?
"I'll put a bit of power there.
I'll put a bit to that one."
But, as we climbed past 4,000ft,
the going started
to get really tough.
Keep going. Keep going.
Thunderbird 2 is still go.
Keep those revs up. Keep
the wheels spinning.
Come on, Jeremy. You
need to get there first.
I do not want to drive
back to Vancouver
with my VelociRaptor being soiled
by Hammond's cheesy,
decomposing bottom.
Oh, my head's come off. Has it?
Well, a man threw a knife at
me but I caught it in my teeth.
Literally, my head came
off. Oh, but I'm OK.
Oh, are you?
In the cock!
Right in the nads! Look at that!
♪ Driving along singing this song...
Come on.
♪.. something in a
winter wonderland. ♪
[BLEEP.]
Situation update, viewers, bit
too close to the edge, there.
I've got to be careful how I move,
otherwise I'll fall into the valley.
'Still, could be worse.'
Whoa! Oh, no!
[BLEEP. BLEEP.]
Whoa!
Faced with the prospect of having to
rescue the world's angriest man...
Where are you, you pair of
[BLEEP] middle-aged [BLEEP]?!
James and I had both decided
to rip out our own fingernails.
Ow!
This made progress much easier.
That feels good.
Temperatures and pressures
are still in the green.
With snow chains fitted, you're
supposed to be gentle,
but, luckily, my colleague
doesn't know what that means.
Dig and claw.
Dig and claw. Come on. Dig in.
Damn and blast.
Come on.
You know you want to do this.
You don't want Richard
Hammond in you.
Oh, no!
'The news was grim.'
[BLEEP].
You are genuinely a bit of
a desperado here, Silverado.
Loving that.
And loving that, as well.
I'm still coming, Richard Hammond.
And you know what?
So was I.
We are underway. Three
wheels on my wagon
and I am still rolling along.
Come on, machine.
Where's James May? Where is May?
Bit of beans there.
Slightly less beans,
there, for the climb.
That's an engine,
and it's not a plane,
it's a car. It's...
That's got to be them!
Where the bloody hell have they been?
Come on.
Do it! Claw!
Stop panicking, just... ease it off.
Really struggling. Really
struggling here.
Come on!
It's Hammond! Hammond is there!
How could it have taken THAT long?
May, bad news. You're going to have
to take Hammond back to Vancouver.
That's a powerful vehicle.
That is a go-anywhere car!
So where the [BLEEP] have you been?
And he's in an appalling
temper. Absolutely shocking.
Where are you going? Well, now what?
Oh, that's your rescue, is it?
Hold on.
That was shocking.
I have seen Thunderbirds and
I never saw Alan flying along
listening to Boston eating
a bar of chocolate.
- No, you say that...
- Neither did I see Virgil
suggesting they stopped
for a cappuccino. They were both
focused on the job in hand.
Yes, but, in that film,
we did prove that your
watch system works
and both James and I completely fell
in love with our pick-up trucks,
- didn't we?
- Yeah, no, this is a very good
point because, let's be honest,
for 12 years, we've looked down our
noses at big American pick-up trucks
but, having spent quite
a few days in them,
we ended up completely besotted.
It's the value that staggers me.
Because American pick-up trucks are
exempt from the gas guzzler tax,
- they are spectacularly cheap.
- Yeah, I know.
I'm surprised there aren't more
people importing them over here.
Yeah, well, I think the problem is
a car this... Vehicle, I should say,
this size wouldn't really work in
Britain and there's another problem.
Excuse me, Hammond.
I think, if you put
something in the back,
every time you pull up
at a set of red lights,
someone is going to nick it.
Yeah, no, you're dead right.
But, even so, I maintain, my
Silverado, it was brilliant.
Well, it was, James, but, let's be
honest, it didn't actually reach
- the top of the mountain, did it?
- No. I wasn't going to mention that.
Actually, just before the end,
it did break a drive shaft.
Yeah, I did wonder if you
were going to mention that,
because it wasn't in the film.
In the end, neither Thunderbird
Fat nor Thunderbird Slow
- actually rescued me.
- That is true.
No, an actual rescue person
had to come and save me,
and can I just talk
about the four days,
four DAYS of misery, I endured
whilst you two dawdled
from breakfast to breakfast
in your heated trucks?
No, I'm sorry. There isn't time.
And, on that bombshell,
we really must end.
Thank you so much for
watching. Good night!