-(Orange)
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la, la-la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ Singin' a song,
la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la ♪
-Thanks a lot.
I'm getting real sick and tired of
being dragged all over the place.
-Whoa! You're the biggest
orange I've ever seen!
-What? I'm not an orange.
-[gasps]
You must be my big brother!
-I'm not your brother.
-Yeah, ya are.
I'm orange, you're orange.
We're both oranges!
-I'm not an orange, I'm a pumpkin.
-Pumpkin?
Don't you mean "plumpkin"?
[laughs]
You're huge!
-Ha, ha, ha, ha, that's real funny.
-Hey, Plumpkin!
-It's Pumpkin!
-Hey! Hey, Plumpkin!
-What?
-How'd you get so plump?
[laughs]
-[groans]
-Hey, Plumpkin,
wanna see a trick?
-Not really.
-[burps, laughs]
-Yeah, that's not even a trick.
-Hey, Plumpkin!
-It's Pumpkin!
-What?
-Can you touch your
eyeball with your tongue?
-No.
-You haven't even tried it yet.
Try it! Errl...
-I don't want to try it.
-Errl... almost. Errl...
-Would you stop that?
-I almost got it.
-Orange, knock it off!
-You're not trying.
-Oh, my God, stop it!
-What?
-You know,
I'm a pretty relaxed guy most of the time,
and it takes a lot to get me riled,
but you,
you are driving me crazy,
and I've only been here--
what?--a minute.
You don't shut up!
And it's Pumpkin! Pumpkin!
Not Orange, not Plumpkin,
and I'm not your brother.
What? What is it?
Why are you mumbling
and making that face?
-Knife.
-Huh?
[screaming]
-Somebody should take
that guy's knife away.
Right in the head.
Oh no, he's tearing your insides out.
-[shrieks in agony]
-Hey! Hey, Plumpkin!
Hey, Plumpkin! Hey!
Hey Plumpkin,
somebody carved a face on your butt.
[laughing]
Oh...
Hey, who turned out the lights?
Captioned by SpongeSebastian