[school bell rings]
- GREG PIKITIS.
- YOU'RE THE PARKS
LADY, RIGHT?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
I'M THE PARKS LADY.
LESLIE KNOPE.
AND I'M HERE TO TELL YOU
THAT THIS YEAR, IT ENDS.
UGH, THIS KID
MAKES ME CRAZY.
WE GOT A HISTORY,
GREG AND I.
HE ABSOLUTELY TERRORIZES
THE PARK SYSTEM.
EVERY HALLOWEEN SOMEONE
DEFACES THE STATUE
OF MAYOR PERCY
AND RAMSETT PARK.
AND I KNOW
IT'S GREG PIKITIS,
BUT I'VE NEVER
BEEN ABLE TO PROVE IT.
HE'S LIKE AN INVISIBLE,
ADOLESCENT JAMES BOND
SUPER-VILLAIN
CRIMINAL MASTERMIND.
OR MAYBE SOMEONE ELSE
IS DOING IT.
BUT I REALLY FEEL LIKE
IT'S THIS KID.
GOT THE ENTIRE
PARKS DEPARTMENT WATCHING YOU,
MY BOYFRIEND'S A COP.
SO DON'T EVEN TRY IT.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- OH, I THINK YOU DO.
IT ENDS TODAY, PIKITIS.
IT ENDS...
TO...
DAY.
- THANKS FOR STOPPING BY,
LESLIE. YOU LOOK GREAT.
- THANK YOU.
ENDS TODAY.
[triumphant music]
*
- HEY, PARKS DEPARTMENT.
- YAY, ANN'S HERE.
- UH, JUST
TO REMIND YOU--
TONIGHT, 7:00, MY HOUSE,
IN COSTUME. EVERYBODY IN?
- MM.
- YUP.
- COOL. OKAY.
HALLOWEEN IS
MY FAVORITE HOLIDAY.
IT'S JUST THE BEST.
AND I DON'T HAVE TO WORK.
HEY, SLUTTY TEENAGE GIRLS
DRESSED AS SEXY KITTENS,
PUMP YOUR OWN STOMACHS
THIS YEAR.
OH, ONE MORE THING.
THE PEOPLE IN THIS ROOM NOW
ARE THE PEOPLE I INVITED.
PLUS LESLIE AND DONNA,
SO DON'T TELL ANYBODY.
- WHO'S NOT
INVITED, THEN?
- HEY! WHAT'S GOING ON,
CUPCAKE?
EXCITED ABOUT
THE PARTY TONIGHT.
- OH. OH, YOU'RE COMING.
I WAS JUST ABOUT TO TELL YOU.
- JERRY ALREADY TOLD ME.
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
HOW TINY YOUR COSTUME IS.
WHAT TIME DOES IT START?
- 7:00.
- PERFECT.
- YEAH, IT'S PERFECT.
- CHECK THIS OUT.
THESE ARE ALL
THE POSSIBLE ROUTES
FROM GREG PIKITIS' HOUSE
TO THE STATUE.
- THAT LOOKS LIKE
SOMETHING YOU WOULD FIND
ON THE WALL
OF A SERIAL KILLER.
- IN A WAY THAT'S
A COMPLIMENT.
SHOWS DEDICATION.
- MM.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL
ANYWAY?
I MEAN, A KID
TPs SOME STATUE.
- AND ALL THE TREES
AND ALL THE BENCHES.
IT TAKES US, LIKE, TEN DAYS
TO CLEAN HIS MESS UP.
BUT MORE IMPORTANTLY,
GREG PIKITIS SUCKS,
AND I WANT
TO DESTROY HIM.
- OKAY.
WELL, IF YOU DESTROY HIM EARLY,
PLEASE COME BY.
- I WILL.
HEY, HOW IS SOMEONE GONNA BE
ABLE TO GET THROUGH THAT DOOR?
- OH.
- OH! WHAT THE--
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
- JERRY, RELAX. HERE.
AH, WILLIAM PERCY.
ONE OF PAWNEE'S GREATEST MAYORS,
AND A TRUE HERO.
DURING THE PAWNEE BREAD FACTORY
FIRE OF 1922,
HE RAN BACK
INTO A BURNING BUILDING
AND SAVED THE BELOVED SECRET
RECIPE FOR PAWNEE PUMPERNICKEL.
- DIDN'T, LIKE,
30 PEOPLE DIE IN THAT FIRE?
- HE WASN'T SUPERMAN.
- HE LOOKS LIKE
RON SWANSON.
IS THAT WHO
THIS IS BASED ON?
- NO, IT'S BASED ON
WILLIAM PERCY.
WERE YOU LISTENING
TO WHAT I JUST SAID?
- YES.
- OKAY, ANDY. GOOD NEWS.
YOU'RE OFFICIALLY
ON THE PARKS DEPARTMENT PAYROLL.
$8 AN HOUR.
- WHOO-HOO!
- COMMIT THIS TO MEMORY.
YOU SEE HIM, YOU STOP HIM.
KNOCK HIS HEAD OFF
IF YOU HAVE TO.
- DON'T DO THAT.
BUT I GIVE YOU PERMISSION
TO USE EXCESSIVE FORCE.
- DON'T USE EXCESSIVE FORCE.
- DON'T GO OVERBOARD.
JUST STOP HIM.
BY ANY MEANS NECESSARY.
- NO.
JUST STOP HIM.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
- A WEEK AGO, I HAD NOTHING.
NOW I HAVE A PART-TIME JOB,
I'M GONNA MAKE
32 BUCKS TONIGHT.
I OWE LESLIE
EVERYTHING I HAVE.
WHICH AFTER TONIGHT
WILL BE 39 BUCKS.
[doorbell rings]
- HELLO, ANN.
- HEY.
- AM I EARLY?
- NOPE, YOU ARE
RIGHT ON TIME.
- I LIKE YOUR COSTUME.
- OH, THANKS.
RAGGEDY ANN.
IT WAS ONE OF MY FAVORITE BOOKS
WHEN I WAS A KID.
- HMM.
- * HE DID
THE MONSTER MASH *
- * THE MONSTER MASH
- I'M A PIRATE.
- RIGHT.
OH, HEY, DR. HARRIS.
HOW ARE YOU?
- ANN.
- THANKS.
UM, THIS IS RON SWANSON
FROM THE PARKS DEPARTMENT.
I KNOW HIM FROM THAT THING
THAT I'M DOING.
THIS IS DR. HARRIS.
- YOU'RE A DOCTOR.
- YEAH.
- I MEANT YOUR COSTUME.
- I GOT IT.
*
- WORLDS COLLIDING.
ALWAYS AWKWARD.
- 8:22 P.M.
SUSPECT STILL WITH FRIENDS
IN PARKING LOT.
HE LOOKS OBNOXIOUS
AND IRRITATING
EVEN FROM
A GREAT DISTANCE.
- UH, CONFIRMED.
NORMALLY I HATE
WORKING ON HALLOWEEN, BUT, UH,
IT'S NICE HANGING OUT
WITH LESLIE.
YOU KNOW, SHE'S FOCUSED,
SHE'S COMMITTED,
AND, UH, SHE MADE OUT
WITH ME IN MY COP CAR.
IT WAS PRETTY NEAT.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE SAID THAT.
THAT'S CLEAR TO ME NOW.
*
- HEY, GUYS.
- HEY.
REMEMBER
MY BOYFRIEND DEREK?
AND HIS BOYFRIEND BEN?
- YEAH, HI.
IT'S TOTALLY OKAY
THAT YOU DIDN'T WEAR A COSTUME.
- I DID.
I'M A STRAIGHT PERSON.
- HEY. SORRY I'M LATE.
- SEE?
- SORRY IT'S A LITTLE BIT
LAME RIGHT NOW,
BUT WE'LL GET IT GOING.
- I PASSED UP A GAY
HALLOWEEN PARTY TO BE HERE.
DO YOU KNOW HOW MUCH FUN
GAY HALLOWEEN PARTIES ARE?
LAST YEAR I SAW
THREE JONAS BROTHERS
MAKE OUT WITH
THREE ROBERT PATTINSONS.
IT WAS AMAZING.
- SO YOU'RE THE MARK
THAT ANN IS DATING.
- I SUPPOSE THAT I AM.
- WE'RE VERY PROTECTIVE OF ANN.
WE LOOK OUT FOR HER.
- SO YOU KIND OF
DROPPED THE BALL
WITH ANDY, THEN,
DIDN'T YOU?
- OH, ANDY.
- I LOVED ANDY.
OH, SUCH A SWEETHEART.
IS ANDY COMING TONIGHT?
- YOU SHOULD
GET BACK WITH ANDY.
- WHO NEEDS A DRINK?
I DO.
- SUSPECT LAUGHING
WITH FRIENDS
AND PLAYING WITH
HIS STUPID SKATEBOARD
IN A SNIDE,
TURD-ISH MANNER.
- "TURD-ISH"?
- YES. LIKE A TURD.
LIKE A LITTLE TURD.
- HEY, LISTEN.
YOUR SCARE TACTICS
CLEARLY WORKED,
YOU GOT ANDY
GUARDING THE STATUE,
WHY DON'T WE GO
TO ANN'S PARTY?
HAVE A LITTLE FUN.
OH, UH, WE WANTED
TO COVER THAT BLOCK ANYWAY.
WANTED A POLICE PRESENCE
ON IT, SO THAT'S--
THIS IS WITHIN THE BOU--
UH, CONFINES OF--
- SURE, LET'S GO.
- YEAH? OKAY.
- YEAH.
WE'LL GO BY MY OFFICE
AND PICK UP MY COSTUME.
- GOT IT.
- CAN'T WE JUST
FIRE A WARNING SHOT
OVER HIS HEAD
AS WE DRIVE BY?
- NO, BABE,
DON'T TOUCH THAT.
- UGH...
LEAVING LOCATION.
LOOK AT STUPID SUSPECT.
I HATE SUSPECT.
WHERE ARE MY KEYS?
- LOOKS LIKE IT'S OPEN.
- REALLY?
[gasps]
PIKITIS!
- WE'VE BEEN TAILING
THAT KID FOR A COUPLE HOURS.
I MEAN, IT MUST'VE
BEEN SOMEBODY ELSE.
- IT WAS PIKITIS.
BELIEVE ME NOW.
- THAT DOESN'T
MEAN ANYTHING TO ME.
- THIS IS A PEACH PIT.
- OKAY.
- HE WAS EATING A PEACH
WHEN I WENT TO GO TALK TO HIM.
THIS IS HIS
ACE OF SPADES.
THIS IS HIS CALLING CARD,
THIS IS WHAT HE LEAVES
ALL HIS VICTIMS.
AND IT'S STILL WARM.
OKAY, GO AND ARREST HIM
AND SEND THIS TO THE LAB.
- WE DON'T HAVE A L-LAB.
- HI, APRIL.
OKAY, YOU'RE UNDERAGE.
- YOU'RE NOT.
- HEY.
YEAH, I'M GONNA LEAVE.
- OH, OKAY.
- THIS ISN'T THAT FUN.
- DIDN'T NEED
TO TELL ME THAT.
- I'M GONNA
TAKE THIS HOME.
NOBODY WAS DRINKING IT,
SO I'M GONNA TAKE IT.
- OKAY.
- GONNA TAKE THIS TOO.
BEEN MEANING TO READ IT.
- [sighs]
- OKAY, THIS ISN'T
STRICTLY LEGAL.
WE CONSULT HIM
FOR MAYBE AN HOUR,
AND THEN I GOT
TO LET HIM GO.
- YOU TALK TO HIM FIRST.
YOU HAVE A SCARY FACE.
- HEY.
- NO, IN A GOOD WAY.
SCARY CUTE.
- YEAH?
- GO TALK TO HIM.
- OKAY.
- I DIDN'T DO THIS, MAN.
I PROMISE.
- SON, I'M A POLICE OFFICER,
OKAY, YOU SHOULDN'T LIE TO ME.
- I'M NOT.
I'VE NEVER BEEN HERE BEFORE.
AND WHY WOULD I DO THIS?
- BECAUSE YOU'VE HAD RUN-INS
WITH MISS KNOPE IN THE PAST.
[cell phone rings]
JUST A SECOND.
YEAH?
- ASK HIM ABOUT THE PEACH PIT.
- THIS ISN'T
ONE-WAY GLASS, YOU KNOW.
I CAN SEE YOU.
YOU KNOW, I LIKE KNOPE.
I SCREW WITH HER
'CAUSE SHE GETS ALL RILED UP.
AND HER FACE GETS
ALL SCRUNCHED UP LIKE THIS.
BUT I LIKE HER.
SHE'S ALL RIGHT.
[laughs]
YOU SEE?
- WHAT?
- I SPENT THE WHOLE DAY
DECORATING THIS PLACE,
AND EVERYBODY'S
IN THE KITCHEN.
WHY IS EVERYONE
ALWAYS IN THE KITCHEN?
- I THINK
IT'S GOING FINE.
- IT'S SO QUIET.
OH, MY GOD,
OH, MY GOD, OH, MY GOD.
THIS IS A TOTAL FAILURE.
THIS PARTY IS A FAILURE.
OH, MY GOD.
- NO, NO, IT'S NOT
A FAILURE, ANN, COME ON.
- ANN, DO YOU HAVE
ANY MOUNDS?
BECAUSE ALL I CAN FIND
ARE ALMOND JOYS.
AND ALMONDS
GIVE ME THE SQUIRTS.
- UGH.
- HEY, I'M HERE.
STATUE'S FINE.
"CRAPPY HALLOWIENERS."
THAT'S HILARIOUS.
WHERE'S THE KID?
- IN THE CONFERENCE ROOM,
TRYING TO HIDE
HIS OBVIOUS GUILT.
- LESLIE, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO TELL YOU.
I DON'T THINK HE DID IT.
- YEAH, HE DID,
AND WE NEED A CONFESSION.
OKAY, ANDY AND I
ARE GOING TO TAKE A WALK.
AND IT'S GONNA BE JUST YOU,
PIKITIS, AND THESE PLIERS.
- LOOK, I'M NOT GONNA
TORTURE THIS KID.
- NOBODY SAID TORTURE.
- WHY DON'T YOU LET ME
TAKE A RUN AT HIM, BOSS?
IN ORDER TO THINK
LIKE ONE OF THESE GUYS,
YOU HAVE TO
THINK LIKE THEM.
- YEAH, HE'S NEVER
SEEN YOU BEFORE.
SO IMPLY THAT YOU'RE
SOMEONE VERY IMPORTANT,
AND THAT YOU CAN
MAKE HIS LIFE HELL.
- [clears throat]
GREG PIKITIS.
WOULD YOU LIKE
SOME BOILING HOT COFFEE?
IN THE FACE?
- MY NAME
IS BERT MACKLIN.
I'M WITH THE [bleep] FBI.
- OOH. ARE THESE
THE SAME KIND OF CHIPS?
- HEY!
WHAT'S UP, GORGEOUS?
- PERFECT.
- GET YOUR RAGGEDY ASS
OVER HERE, GIRL.
- HEY, TOM. MAD HATTER?
- T-PAIN, BABY.
* SHE POPPIN', SHE ROLLIN',
SHE ROLLIN' *
* SHE CLIMBIN' THE POLE AND
I'M IN LOVE WITH THE STRIPPER *
THIS IS NOT A STRIPPER,
IT'S MY WIFE WENDY.
YOU REMEMBER HER.
- HI. THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR INVITING US.
- SURE.
- SHE'S A SURGEON
AT COUNTY GENERAL.
AND SHE'S SUPER HOT.
- WELL, THANK YOU
FOR BEING A DOCTOR
AND NOT COMING
DRESSED AS A DOCTOR.
- OH, MY GOD, WHO'D BE
BORING ENOUGH TO DO THAT?
- ANN,
WHAT HAPPENED HERE?
DID YOU TELL EVERYONE
THEY'RE GONNA HAVE TO
GET A BONE MARROW
TRANSPLANT TOMORROW?
THEY LOOK MISERABLE.
THIS PARTY'S A DISASTER.
- NO, IT'S NOT.
- YES, IT IS.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
WE CAN FIX THIS.
- TOTALLY.
- GIVE US A SECOND.
- YOU ARE THE STUPIDEST
HUMAN BEING I HAVE EVER--
- [sighs]
- SHUT UP!
- LOOKS LIKE ANDY'S
WEARING HIM DOWN.
I'M GONNA
GO FINISH HIM OFF.
- THAT IS THE DUMBEST THING
I HAVE EVER HEARD.
- WHY DON'T YOU JUST
SHUT UP FOR A SECOND?
- WHAT'S GOING ON
IN HERE?
- HE'S A JERK!
HE IS BEING SUCH A JERK!
THAT'S AN AWFUL THING
TO SAY TO A HUMAN BEING!
- ARE YOU CRYING?
- NO, I'M--
I AM NOT CRYING, OKAY?
I'M--I'M ALLERGIC TO JERKS!
- OKAY, ANDY, OUT.
- FINE! I DON'T EVEN CARE!
IT'S STUPID!
- OKAY.
THE GLOVES ARE COMING OFF.
- WH--WHAT'S THAT?
- I THINK YOU KNOW WHAT THAT IS.
WHEN I CAME TO VISIT YOU
AT THE SCHOOL
YOU WERE EATING A PEACH.
THEN MY OFFICE
GETS VANDALIZED
AND SOMEBODY LEAVES
A PEACH PIT ON MY DESK.
I DON'T THINK
THAT'S A COINCIDENCE, GREG.
- WOW. YOU NAILED ME.
I MEAN, THERE IS NO WAY THAT TWO
DIFFERENT PEOPLE COULD'VE EATEN
THE SAME FRUIT IN THE SAME DAY
IN THE SAME AREA OF INDIANA.
NEVER MIND THAT I WAS
ACTUALLY EATING A PLUM
WHEN YOU SAW ME EARLIER.
- I KNOW YOU DID THIS.
I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU SAY.
I DON'T CARE THAT YOU WERE
IN THE PARKING LOT ALL NIGHT,
SOMEHOW YOU FOUND
A WAY TO GET IN HERE.
- WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT I WAS
IN THE PARKING LOT ALL NIGHT?
- BECAUSE
I FOLLOWED YOU, GENIUS!
- IF YOU FOLLOWED ME ALL NIGHT,
THEN YOU KNOW THAT IT WASN'T ME!
NO! WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM?
- LOOK, I'VE BEEN VERY CIVIL,
BUT I WILL WATERBOARD YOU.
- NO, NOPE.
I DON'T THINK
SHE WOULD MAKE A GOOD COP.
I-I WOULD BE FRIGHTENED
TO LIVE IN A TOWN
THAT SHE'S
THE COP OF, FRANKLY.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- ANN, DO YOU WANT ME
TO LIVEN THINGS UP OR NOT?
- OF COURSE I DO.
- ALL RIGHT, THEN RELAX.
TURN OFF ALL THE LIGHTS
THAT DON'T HAVE COLORED BULBS.
[Flo Rida's Jump]
ALL RIGHT, Y'ALL.
TAKE THE PIGS IN A BLANKET
AND PUT 'EM TO SLEEP,
IT'S TIME TO GET WILD!
GET THIS FURNITURE
OUT OF HERE, Y'ALL,
WE'RE MAKING
A DANCE FLOOR.
COME ON, Y'ALL.
PUT THE TURKEY WRAPS DOWN.
WE'RE 'BOUT TO GET WILD.
RON SWANSON
IN THE BUILDING, Y'ALL!
*
- HIS MOM'S GONNA BE HERE SOON.
PLEASE, DAVE, JUST ARREST HIM.
- ON WHAT CHARGE?
- JUST HANDCUFF HIM
TO SOMETHING.
- GREGGY? GREG!
GREGSY.
- MOM.
- MRS. PIKITIS.
HI, I'M LESLIE KNOPE.
THIS IS OFFICER SANDERSON.
- AND BERT MACKLIN. FBI.
- WHAT THE HELL DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
YOU CAN'T JUST HOLD
A 16-YEAR-OLD KID
AGAINST HIS WILL.
- WELL, WE WERE
TRYING TO QUESTION HIM
ABOUT THIS VANDALISM.
- DO YOU HAVE
ANY EVIDENCE?
- YES. TWO WORDS.
- NO. NO, WE DON'T--
- PEACH PIT.
- HIS DNA IS ALL OVER IT,
I ASSUME.
- WE DON'T KNOW THAT.
- WE CAN GET IT TESTED,
AND IF IT MATCHES YOUR DNA,
THEN YOU'RE GOING AWAY
FOR A LONG TIME.
- IS THIS A JOKE?
- NO.
- I'M CALLING
YOUR SHIFT COMMANDER.
MONDAY MORNING,
I AM CALLING YOUR BOSS.
I DON'T KNOW
WHO TO CALL ABOUT YOU--
- PRESIDENT
OF THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA.
- FINE!
AND IF ANY OF YOU EVER
COME NEAR MY SON AGAIN,
I SWEAR TO GOD I WILL SUE YOU
AND EVERYONE IN THIS BUILDING.
COME ON, HONEY.
- LET 'EM THINK THEY'VE LOST US.
THEN--
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- I GOT TO GO TELL MY BOSS WHY
I ILLEGALLY DETAINED A TEENAGER.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE
GOTTEN INVOLVED WITH THIS.
IT'S JUST--
JUST BAD POLICE WORK.
- YEAH, IT WAS
BAD FBI WORK TOO.
MY BAD.
- TONIGHT THE "T" IN T-PAIN
STANDS FOR "TOM HAVERFORD"!
NURSES VERSUS DOCTORS.
ON MY MARK.
THREE, TWO, ONE...
VODKA!
[cheering]
- SON.
THAT IS ONE
HELL OF A COSTUME.
- THANKS.
- DAMN, THAT'S GOOD.
NICE PARTY.
- THANKS.
- WHY WOULD
ANYONE DO THIS?
- KIDS ARE KIDS.
EVERYBODY DOES STUPID STUFF
LIKE THIS IN HIGH SCHOOL.
- I DIDN'T.
- YEAH, BUT YOU WERE
PROBABLY A NERD, THOUGH, HUH?
- HEY.
- LESLIE, I MEAN THAT
IN A GOOD WAY.
LOOK AT YOU NOW.
YOU'RE THE COOLEST PERSON
I'VE EVER MET.
I EVEN MET
JOHN COUGAR MELLENCAMP ONCE.
- ANDY, WHY DON'T YOU GO HOME?
I'LL FINISH CLEANING THIS UP.
- NO WAY.
YOU GOT ME A JOB. YOU'RE HELPING
ME TURN MY LIFE AROUND.
I GO HOME
WHEN YOU GO HOME.
- UH, IT'S--
IT'S CITY PLANNING.
IT'S MOSTLY, LIKE,
REGULATING THINGS
AND JUST MAKING SURE
PEOPLE OBEY THE CITY CODE.
- YOU WANT TO GET OUT OF HERE?
GO BACK TO MY PLACE?
- WHAT? NO.
I'M DATING ANN.
- GOOD. THAT WAS A TEST.
YOU PASSED.
LET'S CELEBRATE
YOU PASSING THE TEST,
OVER A DRINK AT MY PLACE.
- NO. STILL NO.
- YOU PASSED
A SECOND TEST.
BUT WE'RE STILL
WATCHING YOU.
[slow r&b music]
- SO YOU WANT TO GET OUT
OF HERE, GO BACK TO MY PLACE?
*
- HEY, RON.
- HELLO, WENDY.
BOY, YOU AND TOM REALLY
TURNED THE PARTY AROUND.
- OH. WE HAVE
A GOOD TIME TOGETHER.
TOM TOLD ME THAT YOU KNOW
ABOUT OUR GREEN CARD MARRIAGE,
AND I JUST--
I JUST WANT TO SAY THANK YOU
FOR NOT TELLING ANYONE.
- NO WORRIES.
I'D HATE FOR YOU
TO HAVE TO GO BACK TO CANADA.
ALL THE--ALL THAT
SOCIALIZED MEDICINE UP THERE.
- WENDYLICIOUS,
WHERE YOU BEEN?
- I WAS JUST THANKING RON FOR,
YOU KNOW, NOT TELLING ANYONE.
- OH, YEAH. THANK YOU.
THAT WAS COOL OF YOU.
- YOU KNOW, YOU WON'T HAVE TO
KEEP IT A SECRET MUCH LONGER
BECAUSE IN A FEW MONTHS
WE CAN SPLIT UP
WITHOUT RAISING
ANY EYEBROWS.
AND WE'LL INVITE YOU
TO THE DIVORCE PARTY.
- OH, MAYBE GREG
IS INNOCENT.
IF THAT'S THE CASE,
THEN THERE'S ANOTHER KID
OUT THERE WHO'S TORMENTING ME.
- MAYBE.
- I BELIEVE THAT YOU'RE
INNOCENT UNTIL
PROVEN GUILTY IN THIS COUNTRY.
THAT'S THE CORNERSTONE
OF DEMOCRACY.
- SURE.
- ON THE OTHER HAND,
GREG PIKITIS IS A LITTLE PUNK.
I KIND OF WANT TO
TP HIS HOUSE.
- LET'S DO IT.
- [laughing]
WAIT, WAIT, THIS IS FUN,
THIS IS FUN, WHAT DO I DO?
- YOU JUST GRAB
THE TOILET PAPER,
UNROLL IT A LITTLE BIT
LIKE THIS,
THROW IT OVER THE TREE.
- THIS IS FOR
MAYOR PERCY,
THIS IS FOR
THE PARKS DEPARTMENT OFFICE,
THIS IS FOR POOPING
ON THE HANDBALL COURT!
- [clucks]
- [squeaks]
YEAH! THIS IS REALLY FUN,
BUT I DON'T CONDONE IT!
[breathing frantically]
- BYE, GUYS.
YOU'RE THE MAN, SWANSON.
THANKS FOR COMING.
- ARRR...
- ANN.
- DUDE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
- DON'T MENTION IT.
- ALSO, TOM,
YOUR WIFE IS SUPER COOL.
SO WELL DONE.
- YEAH,
SHE'S PRETTY GREAT, RIGHT?
- YEAH, I DON'T KNOW
HOW YOU LANDED THAT CHICK,
BUT SHE'S AWESOME.
NICE WORK.
YOU'RE LUCKY.
- HI. YOU READY TO GO?
- YES.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WE HAD SO MUCH FUN.
- BYE. THANK YOU.
- 'BOUT TO HEAD HOME
AND HAVE CRAZY SEX.
- THAT'S COOL. I DON'T--
- YAY!
[laughs]
- [laughs]
[police siren sounds]
FIVE-0! FIVE-0!
- I SEE YOU
IN THERE, ANDY.
LESLIE,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- OH, BOY.
- THAT'S THEM, OFFICER.
RIGHT THERE.
- OH, MY GOD. OH, NO.
I'M SO SORRY.
I THINK WE HAVE THE WRONG HOUSE.
- WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
- IT'S REALLY HARD
TO EXPLAIN,
BUT WE WERE TRYING
TO GET REVENGE
ON THIS KID GREG PIKITIS,
AND WE THOUGHT
THIS WAS HIS HOUSE,
BUT I GUESS WE GOT
THE ADDRESS WRONG.
- I'M GREG'S MOM.
- YOU ARE?
- YES.
OH, DID HE HIRE A FAKE MOM AGAIN
TO GET HIM OUT OF TROUBLE?
- WHAT?
- WHENEVER HE GETS IN TROUBLE
HE GOES ON CRAIGSLIST
AND HIRES A WOMAN TO PLAY
HIS MOTHER AND BAIL HIM OUT.
OH, THAT LITTLE S-O-B.
GREG! GREGORY!
- I KNEW IT!
- OH, MY GOD.
- DUDE.
THAT KID IS AMAZING.
- HE'S NOT IN HIS ROOM.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE HE IS.
- I DO.
- MAKE SURE YOU GET THAT.
- HEY!
- LET THEM GO!
STAY ON THE LEADER!
[panting]
- OOH...
I AM GONNA
WRING YOUR NECK!
- HOW DID YOU GET
INTO THE PARKS DEPARTMENT?
I HAVE TO KNOW.
- MAYBE THE FBI
CAN FIGURE IT OUT.
- [laughs]
I'M NOT EVEN IN THE FBI, STUPID.
- WOW. YOU'RE AMAZING.
- HEY! YOU'RE GOING TO JAIL
FOR A VERY LONG TIME.
- YOU CAN'T--
- HE'S NOT GONNA GO TO JAIL,
YOU KNOW, HE'S A MINOR.
- WE'LL LET
THE JURY DECIDE.
- IT'S NOT GONNA BE A JURY,
IT'S HIS--
- THEN THE JUDGE WILL
DECIDE WHERE HE GOES.
- LOOK, HE'S GONNA DO PROBATION,
HE'S A MINOR--
- DAVE,
JUST LET ME HAVE THIS.
- WOW, NICE WORK, KNOPE.
- YEAH, THAT IS AMAZING.
- THANKS.
BUT THE THING THAT'S DRIVING ME
NUTS IS HOW DID HE DO IT?
- IF YOU DESTROY HIM EARLY,
PLEASE COME BY.
- I WILL.
- HOW IS SOMEONE GONNA BE ABLE
TO GET THROUGH THAT DOOR?
- OH! WHAT THE--
- I MEAN, WE WERE HERE
ALL AFTERNOON.
HOW DID HE GET IN?
FIRST OF ALL, WE ALWAYS
LOCK THE DOORS WHEN WE LEAVE.
AND DAVE AND I
TAILED PIKITIS
FROM THE MOMENT
HE LEFT HIS HOUSE AT 7:00 P.M.
TO THE MOMENT
WE CAME BACK HERE.
DOES HE HAVE
A LOOK-ALIKE OR SOMETHING?
DID HE HAVE AN ACCOMPLICE?
I MEAN, DID HE HAVE HELP?
HOW DID THAT
LITTLE TURD DO IT?
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com