- AND TO MY WIFE,
I APOLOGIZE.
ALL I CAN SAY IS,
I WASN'T JUST HAVING SEX.
I WAS MAKING LOVE
TO A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN...
AND HER BOYFRIEND,
AND A THIRD PERSON
WHOSE NAME I NEVER LEARNED.
FURTHERMORE,
IT WAS WRONG OF ME TO SAY
I WAS BUILDING HOUSES
FOR THE UNDERPRIVILEGED
WHEN I WAS ACTUALLY
HAVING FOUR-WAY SEX
IN A CAVE IN BRAZIL.
- I BET CAVE SEX IS IN-SANE.
- WHY?
- BECAUSE OF THE ECHOES
AND THE HUMIDITY.
- IN MY DEFENSE,
IT WAS MY BIRTHDAY,
AND I REALLY WANTED TO DO IT.
- I THINK IT'S A REAL SHAME
WHEN PEOPLE FOCUS ON
THE TAWDRY DETAILS OF A SCANDAL.
PERSONALLY, ALL I CARE ABOUT
IS COUNCILMAN DEXHART'S
POLICIES,
NOT WHETHER HE WAS HIGH
ON NITROUS AND COCAINE
DURING THE CAVE SEX...
WHICH, BY THE WAY,
I HEARD HE WAS.
- ONE MORE SHOCKING REVELATION
IN A STORY
THAT JUST
WON'T STOP UNFOLDING.
IT TURNS OUT
COUNCILMAN DEXHART
MAY HAVE ALSO HAD SEX
WITH A PROSTITUTE
IN THE LIMOUSINE
ON THE WAY TO AND FROM
THE PRESS CONFERENCE
WHERE HE APOLOGIZED
FOR HAVING AN AFFAIR.
- WHY DOES ANYBODY WANT TO RUN
FOR PUBLIC OFFICE?
YOU'RE JUST ASKING TO HAVE
YOUR ENTIRE LIFE EXPOSED.
- WELL, IF YOU'RE SQUEAKY CLEAN,
LIKE I AM,
THERE'S NO PROBLEM.
- TOM, YOU'RE MARRIED, AND YOU
HIT ON WOMEN CONSTANTLY.
- YEAH, BUT I'VE
NEVER SEALED THE DEAL.
JUST WINDOW SHOPPING.
YOU CAN FLY TO BRAZIL,
JUST DON'T ENTER THE CAVE.
AM I RIGHT?
UP TOP.
[triumphant music]
*
- I'M SURE THAT YOU THINK
THAT YOU'RE CLEAN,
BUT I BET THAT WE COULD FIND
SOMETHING ON YOU.
- I CHANGED MY NAME,
WHICH IS LEGAL,
AND ONCE IN HIGH SCHOOL,
A GIRL BEAT ME
IN A WRESTLING MATCH.
THAT'S IT.
I BET ANYTHING
I CAN FIND WORSE STUFF
ON ALL YOU GUYS.
- ARE YOU SUGGESTING A GAME?
I'M IN.
- I'M IN.
- I'M OUT.
- NOT AN OPTION, JERRY.
YOU'RE GOING DOWN.
- NO, SERIOUSLY, I REALLY
DON'T WANT TO PLAY.
- NO, NO, SERIOUSLY,
YOU ARE PLAYING.
WE'RE GONNA NAIL YOU.
- I WILL PLAY, TOO.
IF ONLY TO PROVE
THAT I CAN FIND MORE DIRT ON YOU
THAN YOU CAN ON ME.
- THAT'S WHY WE'RE ALL PLAYING.
- YOUR DESK IS OVER THERE.
- I LOVE GAMES THAT TURN PEOPLE
AGAINST EACH OTHER.
- YOU GUYS WILL NEVER BELIEVE
WHAT I JUST FOUND
ON JERRY'S FACEBOOK.
- A FRIEND. BURN.
- OKAY, AGAIN,
I'D REALLY RATHER NOT PLAY.
- HEY, GUYS,
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
- TRYING TO SEE WHO HAS
THE LEAST AMOUNT OF DIRT ON THEM
IN CASE SOMEONE WANTS
TO RUN FOR OFFICE.
- OH, WELL, IT AIN'T JERRY,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
HE'S GOT A COUPLE
OF 3-5-9s ON HIM.
PUBLIC URINATION.
- I DON'T LIKE THIS GAME.
JUST DON'T LIKE IT.
- HE'S PROBABLY GONNA GO
ANGER PEE IN THE COURTYARD.
- [laughs]
- WELL, YOU CRAZY PARK PEOPLE,
UH, I'M OUT OF HERE.
LESLIE, I'LL--
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
- TOMORROW WILL BE
OUR FIRST OFFICIAL--
FIRST DATE.
- ROGER THAT.
- COPY. OVER AND OUT.
DAVE AND I ARE GOING
ON OUR FIRST DATE TOMORROW.
I'M NOT NERVOUS.
WHY SHOULD I BE NERVOUS?
WE'RE JUST TWO PEOPLE
GOING ON A FIRST DATE.
THERE'S NOTHING
TO BE NERVOUS ABOUT.
[cell phone rings]
AAH!
THAT WAS MY PHONE.
- HEY.
- HI THERE.
WHAT ARE YOU, UH...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- JUST HAVING LUNCH
WITH LESLIE.
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
- I'M LOOKING
FOR SCANDALOUS INFORMATION
ABOUT MY CO-WORKERS
FOR A GAME THAT WE'RE PLAYING.
- MY TAXES PAY YOUR SALARY,
RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- COOL.
AND HE LOOKED UP AT ME,
AND HE SAID, "THANK YOU.
YOU SAVED MY LIFE."
- YEAH. HEY, LISTEN,
I'M REALLY NERVOUS
ABOUT THIS DATE TOMORROW NIGHT.
DO YOU HAVE, LIKE, A FIRST DATE
OUTFIT I COULD BORROW?
LIKE, I DON'T KNOW,
PAIR OF CARGO PANTS.
- YEAH, I WOULDN'T GO
WITH A CARGO PANT.
- WHAT ABOUT,
LIKE, A SEXY HAT?
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THAT EVEN IS.
- HELPING ALREADY.
- DO YOU WANT TO JUST COME BY
AFTER WORK TODAY?
- SURE, YEAH. TONIGHT?
SEVERAL HOURS FROM NOW?
[sighs]
- OR YOU COULD JUST
COME OVER NOW?
- I THINK THAT WOULD BETTER.
THAT WOULD GIVE US MORE TIME.
LET'S GO.
- OH, WHAT YOU DOING, GUYS?
LOOKING FOR DIRT ON ME?
NO POINT.
GIVE UP NOW.
OH, WAIT,
THERE IS THIS.
EVERYBODY, I BOUGHT
A CROISSAN'WICH THIS MORNING.
THIS ISN'T EVEN A REAL RECEIPT,
JUST A SCRAP OF PAPER.
- TALIBAN ROBES!
- WHAT? WHERE'D YOU GET
THAT PHOTO FROM?
- HEY, TOM,
NICE TALIBAN ROBES.
- THOSE AREN'T TALIBAN ROBES.
THAT'S FROM HALLOWEEN
TEN YEARS AGO.
I WAS DRESSED LIKE A JEDI.
- I'M SURE THAT THE VOTERS WOULD
BE ABLE TO TELL THE DIFFERENCE.
- MM, LOOKS TO ME
LIKE YOU'RE IN THE TALIBAN.
- WELL, DID EVERYBODY KNOW
THAT RON'S EX-WIFE TAMMY
IS ACTUALLY HIS SECOND EX-WIFE
NAMED TAMMY?
THAT'S RIGHT.
RON HAS TWO EX-WIVES,
EACH NAMED TAMMY.
- BOTH OF THEM BITCHES.
YES, MY MOM'S NAME
IS TAMMY.
WHAT'S YOUR POINT?
TOM! THAT WAS A JAEGER-SECRET.
YOU JUST BREACHED
A JAEGER-SECRET.
- DAMN!
THIS JUST HEATED UP QUICK.
- * TA-DA
- THAT LOOKS GREAT.
- YEAH?
- WILL YOU BE WEARING IT
OUT OF THE STORE TODAY, MADAME?
- [British accent]
OH, I THINK I WILL, GOOD LADY.
HEY, WHILE I HAVE YOU,
CAN I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
- SHOOT.
- WHAT IF HE ASKS ME
IF I'VE BEEN MARRIED?
- HAVE YOU?
- NO.
- WELL, THEN SAY THAT.
- BUT THEN HE'LL WONDER
WHY I HAVEN'T BEEN MARRIED.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M GONNA DO?
I'M GONNA SAY
THAT I WAS MARRIED,
BUT THE REAL QUESTION IS,
SHOULD I SAY THAT I HAVE KIDS?
GUY LIKE GIRLS
THAT HAVE KIDS, RIGHT?
- WHOA.
- WHAT IF I GET DRUNK
AND I TALK
ABOUT DARFUR TOO MUCH?
OR NOT ENOUGH? WHAT IF I DON'T
BRING UP DARFUR ENOUGH?
- LESLIE, RELAX.
- YEAH.
- OKAY?
- I JUST HAVE A FEW
MORE QUESTIONS FOR YOU, ANN.
"WHAT IF HE SHOWS UP
WITH ANOTHER WOMAN?
"WHAT IF ONE OF MY SLEEVES
CATCHES ON FIRE
"AND IT SPREADS RAPIDLY?
"WHAT IF, INSTEAD OF TIC TACS,
"I ACCIDENTALLY POP
A COUPLE OF AMBIEN,
AND I HAVE TO KEEP PUNCHING
MY LEG TO STAY AWAKE?"
- THOSE ARE
ALL INSANE HYPOTHETICALS,
AND I PROMISE YOU
THEY WON'T HAPPEN.
- THEY HAVE HAPPENED.
ALL OF THESE
HAVE HAPPENED TO ME.
UH, NO, THERE'S MORE.
ONE TIME, I ACCIDENTALLY DRANK
AN ENTIRE BOTTLE OF VINEGAR.
I THOUGHT IT WAS
TERRIBLE WINE.
ONCE, I WENT OUT WITH A GUY
WHO WORE 3-D GLASSES
THE ENTIRE EVENING.
OH, ONE TIME,
I RODE IN A SIDECAR
ON A GUY'S MOTORCYCLE,
AND THE SIDECAR DETACHED
AND WENT DOWN
A FLIGHT OF STAIRS.
ANOTHER TIME, I WENT TO A REALLY
BORING MOVIE WITH A GUY,
AND WHILE I WAS ASLEEP,
HE TRIED TO PULL OUT
ONE OF MY TEETH.
I LITERALLY WOKE UP
WITH HIS HAND IN MY MOUTH.
WE WENT OUT A COUPLE TIMES
AFTER THAT,
BUT THEN HE GOT WEIRD.
I KNOW IT SOUNDS CRAZY.
I'M A GROWN WOMAN, BUT I'M
JUST NOT GOOD ON FIRST DATES.
- OH. OKAY.
OKAY, YOU HAVE A PROBLEM,
AND THIS IS
HOW WE'RE GONNA FIX IT.
- I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
I WEAR AN EARPIECE,
YOU SIT AT A TABLE NEARBY,
YOU SPEAK INTO A MIKE,
YOU TELL ME WHAT TO SAY
ON THE DATE,
BUT LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING,
ANN, IT NEVER WORKS.
- NO, NO, NO,
WE ARE GONNA GO TO A RESTAURANT
AND HAVE A PRACTICE DATE.
I WILL PRETEND TO BE DAVE,
AND YOU WILL PRACTICE ON ME.
- OH, THAT'S
A WAY BETTER IDEA.
HEY, DAVE, IT'S ME.
IT'S LESLIE.
- HI, LESLIE,
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
YOU DON'T WANT TO DO THAT
QUITE YET.
- OH! SO, DAVE,
LET'S BEGIN OUR CONVERSATION.
- WHAT'S ON THE NOTE CARDS?
- THEY'RE POSSIBLE TOPICS
OF CONVERSATION.
WHALES, PARADES,
ELECTRICITY...
AND THE REST ARE BLANK.
- YEAH, WELL, I COULDN'T
THINK OF ANYTHING ELSE.
- LESLIE'S IN WORSE SHAPE
THAN I THOUGHT.
- [laughing]
- IS SHE PRACTICE LAUGHING?
- OH, DAVE.
YOU--AHEM.
- THE DANISH CALL IT
OPPE OG NEDE APPARAT,
WHICH LITERALLY TRANSLATED
MEANS
"THE UP AND DOWN MACHINE."
- WOW. THAT'S A THOROUGH HISTORY
OF THE TEETER-TOTTER.
- NOW I'M GONNA TALK ABOUT
THE LOCAL FLORA AND FAUNA
FOUND IN PAWNEE.
- OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
JUST ASK ME A QUESTION.
JUST TRY TO GET TO KNOW ME.
- OKAY.
I CAN'T THINK OF ANYTHING
TO ASK YOU.
I'M SORRY.
MY MIND IS BLANK.
- JUST ASK ME THE FIRST THING
THAT COMES TO YOUR HEAD.
- HOW BIG IS IT?
- REALLY?
- OH, MY GOD.
- HEY, TOMMY. HI.
YOU READY?
- YES, I AM.
JUST GIVE ME ONE SECOND.
HEY, DONNA,
LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
DO YOU HATE BLACK PEOPLE?
- EXCUSE ME?
- 'CAUSE APPARENTLY
IN 1988,
YOU DONATED MONEY
TO THE PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGN
FOR...
DAVID DUKE!
- THE KKK GUY?
- I GOT A PHONE CALL.
THEY SAID
HE WOULD LOWER TAXES.
- BOOM!
HOW'S IT FEEL
TO LOSE SO HARD?
I'M SORRY, HONEY.
LET'S GET COFFEE.
RE-RON, YOU REMEMBER
MY WIFE, WENDY HAVERFORD.
- OF COURSE.
HOW ARE THINGS AT THE HOSPITAL?
- UH, VERY GOOD,
THANK YOU.
I JUST GOT A PEDIATRIC
SURGERY FELLOWSHIP.
- OH, NICE.
- WE'RE CELEBRATING,
'CAUSE SHE'S SUPER RICH
AND SUPER HOT ALSO.
- OKAY, COME ON, TOMMY.
CUT IT OUT.
- YOU'RE SUPER HOT.
EVERYBODY ELSE
HAS TO DEAL WITH IT.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
SEE YOU LATER, RON.
- I'VE ESTABLISHED
A SCIENTIFICALLY PERFECT
TEN-POINT SCALE
OF HUMAN BEAUTY.
WENDY IS A 7.4,
WHICH IS WAY TOO HIGH
FOR TOM,
WHO IS A 3.8.
TEN IS TENNIS LEGEND
STEFFI GRAF.
- HI, DAVE.
- YOU'RE LATE,
AND I CAN SEE YOUR NIPPLES
THROUGH YOUR DRESS.
- WHAT? NO. REALLY?
- IN NURSING SCHOOL,
WE TOOK A PSYCH COURSE
ON HOW TO TREAT PHOBIAS
WITH A METHOD CALLED
EXPOSURE THERAPY.
SO LIKE IF YOU WERE
AFRAID OF SNAKES,
THEY WOULD IMMERSE YOU
IN A TANK OF SNAKES,
SO I AM GOING TO IMMERSE LESLIE
IN A TANK OF BAD DATE.
YOU'RE 20 MINUTES LATE.
I ALMOST LEFT.
- OKAY. WELL, I WAS, UH...
DROPPING MY NIECE OFF.
- WHAT'S YOUR NIECE'S NAME?
- TORPLE. WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S NOT A NAME.
I DON'T HAVE A NIECE.
- [sighs]
- MY NIECE'S NAME
IS STEPHANIE?
- STOP LYING!
- HEY, LOOK, THERE'S BREAD!
YOU WANT SOME--OH, NO!
OH, I GOT FLOWERS IN YOUR SOUP.
I'M SO SORRY, UM...
JUST--I HAVE TO GO
TO THE, UM...
WHIZZ PALACE.
YOU KNOW, DAVE, THE--
THE PLACE WHERE YOU--
YOU KNOW, THE TOILET THING.
IT'S A BATHROOM!
IT'S CALLED A BATHROOM!
- HEY, MARK, UM,
A LITTLE BIRDY TOLD ME
THAT YOU HAVE
ONE UNPAID PARKING TICKET.
- THAT'S FUNNY,
BECAUSE A LITTLE BIRDY TOLD ME
THAT YOUR ADOPTIVE MOTHER
WAS ARRESTED
FOR MARIJUANA POSSESSION.
- [laughing] OH, SNAP!
- WHAT?
- YOU DIDN'T KNOW THAT, HUH?
- I DIDN'T KNOW
I WAS ADOPTED.
- OH, NO. OH, JERRY.
OH, JERRY, I'M SO SORRY.
- I REALLY DIDN'T
WANT TO PLAY.
- THAT WAS NOT MY INTENTION.
- IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
HE TOTALLY BAITED YOU
WITH THAT UNPAID PARKING TICKET.
- TOM, COULD YOU
COME INTO MY OFFICE?
TOM-MATO SAUCE.
- RON-TANAMO BAY.
- DO BE SEATED,
AND CONGRATULATE ME.
- FOR WHAT?
- WINNING THE GAME.
I JUST FOUND OUT,
THROUGH SOME PRETTY IMPRESSIVE
INVESTIGATING,
THAT YOUR WEDDING
WAS A SHAM.
IT'S A GREEN CARD MARRIAGE.
- THAT'S CRAZY. I WAS BORN
IN SOUTH CAROLINA.
THESE COLORS DON'T RUN,
BABY.
- YES, BUT WENDY
WAS BORN IN OTTAWA...
CANADA!
HER VISA WAS SET TO EXPIRE
THE DAY
AFTER YOU GOT MARRIED
AT THE COUNTY COURTHOUSE
IN FRONT OF THREE STRANGERS
AND NO FAMILY.
- OKAY, WE MET IN COLLEGE.
SHE WANTED TO WORK
IN THE STATES.
SHE COULDN'T GET A PERMIT.
- I KNEW IT. I KNEW YOU COULDN'T
GET A WIFE AS HOT AS HER.
- SERIOUSLY, RON,
GAMES ASIDE,
YOU GOT TO KEEP THIS BETWEEN US.
DON'T TELL ANYBODY, PLEASE.
- COME ON, DON'T WORRY.
I'M NOT GONNA TURN YOU IN.
JUST ADMIT THAT WHEN IT COMES
TO DIGGING UP DIRT,
I BESTED YOU IN THIS GAME.
SAY IT.
SAY "I BESTED YOU."
- FINE, YOU BESTED ME.
IS THAT ALL?
- NO.
I'LL HAVE YOUR WIFE TONIGHT.
- WHAT?
- NO, I'M JUST KIDDING.
GET OUT OF HERE.
- WHY WOULD YOU SAY THAT, DAVE?
THAT DOG WAS LIKE MY
BEST FRIEND, AND WHEN SHE DIED--
- BRRING BRRING,
BRRING BRRING, BRRING.
HEY, TIFFANY.
YEAH, I DEFINITELY
WANT TO SEE YOU TONIGHT.
NO, I CAN'T REALLY TALK
RIGHT NOW,
'CAUSE I'M A DATE
WITH THIS DRIP.
YEAH, I CAN ASK.
HEY, DO YOU WANT TO WATCH
A PORNO AFTER THIS
WITH ME AND MY WIFE?
- NO, DAVE,
'CAUSE YOU'RE DISGUSTING.
- SO IT'S DEFINITELY A NO?
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU'RE BEING SO TERRIBLE.
WE'RE JUST TWO PEOPLE
TRYING TO GO ON A DATE.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE FUN.
IT'S JUST A DATE.
- YOU'RE RIGHT, IT IS.
WELL DONE.
SORRY I HAD TO GET
ALL MEDICAL ON YOU,
BUT NOW YOU SEE THAT
EVEN IF EVERYTHING GOES WRONG,
YOU'LL SURVIVE.
- WELL, WELL, WELL.
YOU COY BASTARD.
- MARK.
- TOM.
- YOU HATE RON, RIGHT?
- NO, I THINK RON IS FINE.
- SO WE'RE ON THE SAME PAGE.
YOU GOT TO HELP ME
TAKE THIS GUY DOWN.
THERE'S GOT TO BE
SOMETHING ON HIM.
- TOM, I'M STARTING TO FEEL
KIND OF GROSS ABOUT THIS GAME.
- IT'S NOT ABOUT THE GAME
ANYMORE.
RON HAS SOME SERIOUS DIRT ON ME.
I NEED TO BALANCE THINGS OUT.
YOU MUST KNOW
HOW THAT FEELS.
YOU GOT TONS OF DIRT
IN YOUR PAST.
PLEASE, YOU GOTTA HELP ME.
- THERE IS A MAN
NAMED DUKE SILVER.
HE HANGS OUT AT A BAR
IN EAGLETON.
HE'S AN OLD FRIEND
OF RON'S.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD ASK HIM.
- THANKS, MAN.
I'M GONNA DIG UP
SO MUCH DIRT ON THIS GUY,
THERE'S GONNA BE WORMS
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
IT SOUNDED SNAPPIER IN MY HEAD.
- YEAH.
- ANN IS SO AWESOME.
I'M LUCKY TO HAVE A FRIEND
WHO WOULD SPEND A WHOLE DAY
BEING SO MEAN TO ME.
CATCH.
I DON'T NEED YOUR DRESS ANYMORE.
I'M GONNA WEAR
MY OWN STUFF.
ME POWER.
- GOOD. YOU'RE
OFFICIALLY FIRST DATE-PROOF.
- THANK YOU, DAVE.
- MM-MM. LISTEN...
IT IS IMPOSSIBLE
THAT HE'S NOT GONNA LIKE YOU.
HE'S GONNA FREAK OUT
ABOUT HOW AWESOME YOU ARE.
- NO, HE'S NOT.
- YES, HE IS.
HE'S GONNA LOVE YOU.
YOU'RE COOL, AND YOU'RE SEXY,
AND YOU'RE FUNNY,
AND YOU'RE SMART.
ANY GUY WOULD BE
LUCKY TO DATE YOU.
- YEAH!
- YEAH! HELL, YEAH!
- HELL, YEAH!
I AM AWESOME!
- YOU ARE AWESOME.
- YEAH!
- AND YOU ARE, TOO.
- THANK YOU.
- YOU ARE, TOO.
- YOU ARE, TOO, ANN!
- OKAY!
YOU'RE AWESOME.
- YOU'RE AWESOME.
HELP, POLICE!
HELP! HELP!
- HEY.
- LOOK, I KNOW TODAY
IS TODAY,
AND IT'S NOT TOMORROW,
BUT I FELT LIKE YOU SHOULD KNOW
THAT I'M AWESOME,
AND YOU'RE LUCKY TO HAVE ME.
AND, UM, I THINK
OUR FIRST DATE TOMORROW'S
GONNA GO AWESOME,
OFF THE CHARTS.
UM, AMAZING. UP TOP.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S DO THIS BITCH!
I'M NOT SCARED.
CAN I COME IN
AND SIT DOWN FOR A BIT?
'CAUSE I WALKED HERE
'CAUSE OF THE DRINKING.
- I DON'T KNOW.
- I DO KNOW.
I'M COMING INSIDE, SO MOVE.
OKAY?
YOU MAKE A BETTER DOOR
THAN A GUY.
- HEY, THIS IS GONNA
SOUND WEIRD.
I'M LOOKING FOR A GUY
NAMED DUKE SILVER.
- YEAH, HE GOES ON
IN A SECOND.
- LADIES, LADIES, LADIES,
IT'S JUST ABOUT THAT TIME.
IT'S WITH THE JAZZIEST PLEASURE
THAT I BRING OUT FOR YOU
MY MAN, MR. DUKE SILVER.
[cheers and applause]
- THANK YOU, DWAYNE.
AS ALWAYS, IT IS A THRILL
TO BE HERE
DURING THIS WITCHING HOUR
WITH YOU LOVELY LADIES.
NOW RELAX
AND LET THE DUKE SILVER TRIO
TAKE YOU ON A LITTLE JOURNEY...
TO YOURSELF.
[playing Foreigner's
I Want To Know What Love Is]
*
- ANN WAS HELPING ME,
BECAUSE I WAS PANICKING
ABOUT TOMORROW.
- DID I SAY SOMETHING
TO MAKE YOU WORRY ABOUT TO--
- NO! NO, JUST THE WHOLE IDEA
OF FIRST DATES
JUST KIND OF FREAK ME OUT.
BUT NOT ANYMORE.
I CAN'T EVEN BELIEVE
THAT I WAS SCARED
TO GO ON A DATE WITH YOU.
I MEAN, YOU SHOULD BE
SCARED OF ME.
- OKAY.
- I THINK I NEED
TO RETURN THIS SWEATER.
I THINK IT FUSED WITH MY SHIRT
IN THE DRYER OR SOMETHING.
- I THINK THAT'S
A SWEATER-SHIRT COMBO.
- I THINK IT'S GOING
PRETTY WELL WITH DAVE.
HE WANTS ME.
I CAN TOTALLY TELL
THAT HE WANTS ME.
- HEY, I'M RIGHT HERE.
YOU KNOW I'M HERE, RIGHT?
- DID YOU SEE MY BRA? HMM?
BEEP-BOOP.
GUESS WHAT? I'M WEARING
THE HOT ONE TOMORROW,
THE BLACK ONE.
- OKAY.
- CAN I USE YOUR BATHROOM?
- YES.
- ARE YOU IMPRESSED
THAT I KNOW WHAT IT'S CALLED?
- MAYBE I OUGHT
TO GIVE YOU A LIFT HOME.
- OH, GOOD. WELL, IN LONDON,
THEY CALL THE ELEVATORS LIFTS,
SO YOU'RE GONNA GIVE ME
AN ELEVATOR HOME?
NO, THANK YOU.
- OKAY, LET'S GO.
- [British accent] OKAY.
LET'S GO DOWN TO THE PUB...
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- AND GET A PINT.
WE'LL PUT OUR KNICKERS
IN THE BEATLE RECORDS.
THIS IS AN ENGLISH ACCENT.
- WHAT I CANNOT BELIEVE
IS DEXHART'S WIFE.
I MEAN, HOW CLUELESS
CAN YOU GET?
HOW DID SHE NOT KNOW
THIS WAS GOING ON?
MORE IMPORTANTLY,
HOW DOES SHE STAY WITH HIM
AFTER ALL THIS?
- HEY, CAN I HELP YOU
AT, UH...
11:48 P.M.?
- OKAY, HERE'S THE WHOLE THING.
HERE ARE ALL MY SKELETONS.
WHEN I WAS 16, I HAD SEX
WITH A MARRIED WOMAN.
- RIGHT.
- WHEN I WAS IN COLLEGE,
I SMOKED A DECENT AMOUNT
OF POT.
- UH-HUH.
- NOTHING INSANE.
- WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?
- WHAT I'M DOING, ANN,
IS I'M TRYING TO TELL YOU
THAT I'VE DONE SOME STUFF
THAT I'M NOT VERY PROUD OF,
AND I LIKE YOU,
SO I WOULD RATHER
YOU NOT FIND OUT ABOUT THIS
FROM ANYONE BUT ME.
THIS WAS A BAD IDEA.
- [laughs]
NO, NO, IT'S...IT'S FINE.
I GET WHAT THIS IS
AND WHY YOU DID IT.
- IS THERE ANYTHING
THAT YOU WOULD LIKE TO SHARE
FROM YOUR PAST TO
SORT OF BALANCE THE SCALES?
- YEAH. ONE TIME, THIS GUY RANG
MY DOORBELL AT MIDNIGHT
TO BRAG ABOUT GETTING LAID
WHEN HE WAS 16, SO I SHOT HIM.
- GOOD NIGHT.
- IT'S BEEN A REAL GIFT MAKING
SONIC LOVE TO YOU TONIGHT.
IF YOU WANT MORE OF THE DUKE,
BOTH MY ALBUMS
ARE FOR SALE HERE--
SMOOTH AS SILVER
AND HI HO, DUKE.
AND LOOK FOR MY NEW CD
NEXT MONTH,
MEMORIES OF NOW.
SO COME SEE ME,
COME TALK TO ME,
COME LOVE WITH ME,
AND MAYBE WE CAN
WALK THROUGH FIRE TOGETHER.
THANK YOU.
GOOD NIGHT
[final note,
applause]
- DUKE! HUGE FAN.
- LOOK, TOM, I IMAGINE
YOU'LL WANT TO TELL EVERYONE
ABOUT THIS,
BUT I HAVE WORKED
PRETTY HARD
TO CULTIVATE
A CERTAIN AUTHORITATIVE
OR INTIMIDATING IMAGE
AROUND THE OFFICE.
- CAN I GET A PICTURE?
- SURE.
- SAY, "I BESTED YOU."
- I BESTED YOU.
- ALL RIGHT.
THANKS FOR LOVIN' THE DUKE.
- THAT--
THAT WAS A LOVELY PHOTO.
- TRUCE?
- TRUCE.
YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
- NO, I'M NOT.
- YOU SHOWED UP
AT THE GUY'S HOUSE,
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT,
DRUNK,
AND YOU DIDN'T EVEN SLEEP
WITH HIM?
- SHOULD I HAVE?
- IT NEVER HURTS.
- GOD.
- HEY.
- HEY!
- UH, AHEM, YOU, UH...
YOU LEFT QUITE A BIT OF STUFF
AT MY PLACE LAST NIGHT--
PURSE AND EARRINGS
AND A SHOE.
- I AM SO SORRY
FOR WHAT HAPPENED LAST NIGHT.
ON MY LIST
OF EMBARRASSING THINGS
THAT I'VE DONE IN MY LIFE,
THAT WAS...
NUMBERS ONE THROUGH SEVEN.
I TOTALLY UNDERSTAND
IF YOU WANT TO CANCEL.
- IT'S OKAY. YOU CAN MAKE IT UP
TO ME TONIGHT
ON OUR SECOND DATE.
- SECOND?
- WELL, YEAH, LAST NIGHT
WAS OUR FIRST DATE,
SO THAT WOULD MAKE TONIGHT
OUR SECOND.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO IT.
8:00?
- 8:00.
- YOU LIKE DANCING?
- YEAH.
- I DON'T LIKE DANCING.
- WE DON'T HAVE TO GO.
- OKAY.
- WELL, WE WENT
ON OUR FIRST DATE,
AND I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW IT,
A.K.A. I NAILED IT.
NO FIRES, NO AMBULANCES.
JUST GOOD OLD-FASHIONED
SHOWING UP DRUNK
AT A GUY'S HOUSE
LATE AT NIGHT.
- HOWEVER, I WANT TO BE CLEAR.
I HAVE NO PLANS
TO RESIGN.
- IS IT WEIRD
THAT MY FEELINGS ARE HURT
THAT NO ONE'S FOUND
ANY DIRT ON ME YET?
HELLO!
I DROVE A RIDING LAWN MOWER
THROUGH A NORDSTROM!
THERE'S VIDEO THAT I TOOK!
NOTHING.
- JERRY, PLASTIC SURGERY?
- I GOT HIT
BY A FIRE ENGINE.
- YOU ARE SO LUCKY.
- HOW?