- WE NOTICED ABNORMAL ACTIVITY
ON YOUR CREDIT CARD,
SO WE JUST
NEED YOU TO CONFIRM OR DENY
SOME OF THE RECENT CHARGES.
- OKAY, THANK YOU.
- $20 TO NETFLIX.
- YUP.
- $20 TO BLOCKBUSTER ONLINE.
- BOTH?
- I NEEDED ALL 11 DISCS OF
GOSSIP GIRL AT THE SAME TIME.
- $120 IN TUITION
TO HOGWARTS SCHOOL
OF WITCHCRAFT AND WIZARDRY.
- THEY GIVE YOU A LITTLE WAND,
AND A DIPLOMA, IT'S FUN.
- WHAT'D YOU MAJOR IN?
- POTIONS.
YOU KNOW, I'M GONNA
TAKE YOU OFF SPEAKERPHONE.
GO AHEAD.
- JESSICA SIMPSON
CLIP-IN HAIR EXTENSIONS.
- NO. OKAY...UM...
I WORE THOSE ONCE.
IT WAS A MONEY-BACK GUARANTEE,
BUT I FORGOT TO RETURN THEM.
- MAN-PILLOW,
THE PILLOW SHAPED LIKE A MAN.
- OH, GOD.
- ALSO SOMETHING
CALLED BUCKET OF CAKE.
- YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK SOMEONE DEFINITELY STOLE
MY CREDIT CARDS
SO WHY DON'T
YOU JUST CANCEL IT?
- DO YOU WANNA HEAR
WHAT ELSE THEY PURCHASED?
- YES.
- NO, UM...YOU DON'T HAVE TO
REFUND ANYTHING.
JUST CANCEL THE CREDIT CARD
AND WE'LL ALL GO ON
WITH OUR LIVES.
THANK YOU.
- SO...WHAT DOES
A MAN-PILLOW LOOK LIKE?
- DANIEL CRAIG.
IT'S FOR MY LOWER BACK.
[triumphant music]
*
[applause]
- MY NAME IS KEITH,
AND I AM YOUR FRIEND.
ARE YOU GUYS MY FRIENDS?
all: YEAH!
- ALL RIGHT.
AWESOME!
IT IS PLAYGROUND TIME!
all: YAY!
[applause]
- WELL, WE'RE HERE IN EAGLETOWN,
IT'S TWO TOWNS OVER.
AND WE'RE ALL
VOLUNTEERING FOR KABOOM!
A SERVICE ORGANIZATION THAT SAYS
IT BUILDS A PLAYGROUND IN A DAY.
- HIGH FIVE,
HIGH FIVE.
- I NEVER TRUST ANYTHING
THAT COMES THAT QUICKLY.
THAT'S WHY
I DON'T EAT MINUTE RICE.
SO THIS WHOLE BUILD-A-
PLAYGROUND-IN-A-DAY THING,
I MEAN THAT'S
JUST A SLOGAN, RIGHT?
- NOPE, ONE DAY, 24 HOURS.
- KEITH, THAT IS SO INCREDIBLE.
- KEITH!
- I MEAN, I WORK IN PARKS,
AND I KNOW HOW HARD IT IS
TO GET SOMETHING DONE.
- NOT IF YOU
HAVE THE KABOOM! SPIRIT.
YOU CAN LOOK AT A PROBLEM AND
YOU CAN EITHER GO
"UH, THIS IS A PROBLEM",
OR YOU CAN KABOOM!
BLOW IT UP AND
TURN IT INTO SOMETHING GREAT.
YOU LITERALLY
"KABOOM!" THE PROBLEM.
[claps twice]
COME ON, PEOPLE!
I SEE MORE
GROUND THAN PLAYGROUND.
[high pitch] KABOOM!
- DON'T DO THAT.
both: ONE, TWO, THREE.
- OOH!
- MAN, THIS IS TOUGH.
- YEAH, BUT JUST
THINK OF ALL THE KIDS
THAT WILL
SWING ON THIS SWING.
FAT KIDS, SKINNY KIDS,
BRAINIACS, SLUTS,
THE GAY DRAMA KIDS, GOTHS,
JOCKS, THE ALTERNATIVE CROWD.
- MM-HMM.
- HEY, LESLIE.
HI.
WHOA, ANN!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- OH, I'M VOLUNTEERING.
I LOVE TO VOLUNTEER.
THE KEY TO VOLUNTEERING?
A LOT OF POCKETS.
FOR PUTTING ALL THE FOOD IN.
THE RED CROSS
HAS AMAZING COOKIES.
I GO THERE ALL THE TIME.
MEALS ON WHEELS
WAS A BONANZA.
SUICIDE HOTLINE,
SURPRISINGLY LAME SPREAD.
THOUGHT I'D GIVE BACK TO THOSE
LESS FORTUNATE THAN MYSELF.
- YOU LIVE IN A PIT.
- NOT ANYMORE.
LIVING WITH
THE DRUMMER OF MY BAND.
LIVING INDOORS.
PRETTY COOL.
NOT TO BRAG.
KINDA HARD NOT TO.
ANYHOW, GOTTA GO.
ME AND AN OLD ASIAN LADY
ARE DOUBLE-TEAMING
SOME MONKEY BARS, SO.
- HEY, LOOK, I GOT A REMOTE
CONTROL AND I'M CONTROLLING YOU.
GO FASTER!
* GO FASTER,
RON'S THE MASTER *
- AH! WELL...
YOU HAVE BEEN
OFFICIALLY KABOOMED.
- WHOA, LOOK AT YOU TWO
AND YOUR BIG KABOOM!
GREAT JOB!
I GOT GIFTS.
- OH!
- THERE YOU GO FOR YOU.
- THANKS.
- AND ONE MORE FOR YOU.
- THANK YOU.
- SO YOU GUYS GONNA
JOIN US TOMORROW IN MUNCIE?
- NO, I WISH,
BUT BACK TO THE REAL WORLD.
- AT LEAST YOU GUYS WILL BE
KABOOMING SOMEWHERE, RIGHT?
REMEMBER...
TAKE A MAN KABOOMING,
HE KABOOMS FOR A DAY.
BUT YOU TEACH A MAN
HOW TO KABOOM...
KABOOM! KABOOM!
KABOOM!
- UH, I'M SO PUMPED!
GOD, I COULD
TAKE ON THE WORLD.
- I COULD PREP, LIKE,
1,000 DIAGNOSTIC TESTS.
- [laughing]
- IN AN HOUR!
- THAT'S THE SPIRIT.
- THERE IT IS--THE PIT.
- MM.
- THERE'S SOMETHING
I WISH I COULD KABOOM!
- WELL, WE ARE.
IT'S JUST A SLOW BOOM.
A SLOWER,
MORE DELIBERATE KABOOM!
- YEAH, TOTALLY.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
- OKAY.
[car door closes]
[sighs]
[exhales]
YOU KNOW
WHAT THIS MESS IS?
THIS IS A LIST OF THINGS
WE HAVE TO COMPLETE
BEFORE WE FILL IN
THE PIT BEHIND ANN'S HOUSE.
YOU KNOW WHAT THIS IS?
THIS IS A KABOOMER.
JERRY, DID YOU USE
PERMANENT MARKER AGAIN ?
- I'M SORRY, GUYS.
[everyone grumbles
over each other]
- OKAY, FORGET IT.
LET'S ALL
PRETEND JERRY WASN'T BORN.
AND THIS IS CLEAN.
HOW DO WE
SPEED UP THE PROCESS?
HOW DO WE KABOOM! IT?
RULES, CODES,
PERMITS, RED TAPE--
I NEVER REALIZED HOW FRUSTRATING
IT IS TO BE IN THE GOVERNMENT.
IN MY NEXT LIFE,
I'M GOING INTO PRIVATE INDUSTRY.
MAYBE STRIP MINING.
OKAY, EVERYBODY TAKE OUT
THEIR THINKING CAPS.
AND RIP THEM UP.
THEN TAKE OUT
YOUR DOING CAPS,
'CAUSE WE'RE GONNA
DO SOMETHING TODAY.
- I HAVE A COUPLE
DOING CAPS IN MY WALLET.
THAT'S WHAT I CALL CONDOMS.
- COME ON, TOM.
FOCUS, PLEASE.
HOW DO WE CUT
THROUGH THE RED TAPE?
AND HOW DO WE GET
THIS PIT FILLED IN? IDEAS?
- WE NEED TO CUT THROUGH THE RED
TAPE AND GET THE PIT FILLED IN.
- YES, TOM.
GOOD.
OKAY, EVERYBODY ELSE NEEDS
TO PARTICIPATE. COME ON, GUYS.
THESE SUGGESTIONS
AREN'T GONNA SUGGEST THEMSELVES.
YES, JERRY?
THIS IDEA BETTER BE GOOD.
ANN?
- I SUPPORT YOU.
- GOOD.
- YOU COULD PETITION
TO EXPEDITE
THE ARCHITECTURAL
REVIEW BOARD PROCESS.
- MARK, BUDDY...
YOU'RE NOT LISTENING TO ME.
I WANT TO KABOOM! IT.
OKAY?
- CAN I TALK TO YOU
OUTSIDE REALLY QUICK?
- SURE.
MARK'S GONNA HELP ME,
SO THANKS FOR NOTHING, JERRY.
GOOD JOB, ANN.
- SO YOU REALLY WANNA
GET THIS PIT FILLED IN, RIGHT?
- YES.
- AND WE'LL DO WHATEVER
IT TAKES?
- MARK, I AM SO SICK
OF MOVING LIKE A SLUG.
I WANNA MOVE LIKE A CHEETAH.
OR A SLUG DRIVING
A REMOTE CONTROLLED CAR.
SOMETHING MORE PLAUSIBLE
THAN THAT, BUT FAST.
- WOULD YOU BREAK THE RULES?
- I WON'T MURDER.
- THAT'S GOOD TO KNOW.
BUT IT'S
ACTUALLY VERY SIMPLE.
IF YOU WANNA FILL IN THE PIT,
JUST GO FILL IT IN.
DON'T ASK FOR PERMISSION,
ASK FOR FORGIVENESS.
- OH, I LIKE THAT.
OKAY, WOW.
SO WHO GIVES ME THE GO AHEAD
TO NOT ASK
FOR PERMISSION, BECAUSE--
- NO, NO, NO.
- IS IT RON?
- NO, IT'S NOBODY.
IT'S NOBODY.
IT'S YOU.
YOU HAVE TO BE BOLD.
- OKAY?
- OKAY, LOOK...
YOU WANNA
GET THE PIT FILLED IN?
THEN GO RENT A BULLDOZER
AND FILL IN THE FREAKING PIT.
- HEY.
- WHAT'S UP?
- SAY YOU HAD A FRIEND
WHO WANTED TO DO SOMETHING GOOD,
BUT A LITTLE RISKY, AND SHE
WAS KIND OF NERVOUS ABOUT IT.
AND THIS FRIEND IS ME.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
- MM, YOU SHOULD DO IT.
AND YOU SHOULD ASK
YOUR FRIEND TO HELP YOU
BECAUSE YOUR FRIEND
TOTALLY HAS YOUR BACK.
AND THAT FRIEND IS ME.
- YOU'LL HELP ME?
- OF COURSE, I'LL DO
ANYTHING I CAN TO HELP.
LET'S DO IT!
[laughing]
- OKAY.
- WHAT ARE WE DOING?
IS IT DANGEROUS?
- WE'RE NOT GOING
TO MURDER ANYONE.
- IT WAS CRAZY.
I DIDN'T GET A SINGLE PERMIT.
NOBODY STAMPED ANYTHING,
ALL I DID WAS ORDER A BACKHOE,
AND IT CAME WITH
A GUY WHO RUNS IT.
I'VE NEVER
RENTED A GUY BEFORE.
WISH I KNEW
ABOUT THAT DURING PROM.
- THERE WAS A GIRL AT MY PROM
WHO WAS KNOWN AS THE BACKHOE.
MARY DUNBAR, SHE'D
LET ANYONE MASSAGE HER BACK.
- I'M SO EXCITED
WE'RE DOING THIS!
AND WE'RE DOING IT
WITHOUT PERMISSION.
WE'RE GIVING OURSELVES
PERMISSION.
- [laughing]
- LOOK!
I HAD THESE HARD HATS MADE.
CHECK IT OUT..."KICK ASS".
- I'LL TAKE THAT ONE.
- OKAY.
OH, MY GOD!
ANN, THIS IS SO COOL!
DO YOU FEEL GIDDY?
- YEAH.
- I'M SO PROUD OF US.
- MS. MONTEGUE, YOU READY?
- I DIDN'T WANNA TELL HIM
MY REAL NAME, YOU KNOW?
[heavy accent]
YEAH.
FIRST SPEECH, EASY--
IMPORTANT MOMENT HERE.
WE ARE ABOUT
TO FILL THIS HOLE NOW.
NOT WITH DIRT, BUT WITH
THE COURAGE OF A THOUSAND LIONS.
AND THE SOLEMN MEMORY
OF ALL OF OUR FRIENDS
WHO HAVE FALLEN IN
THIS CURSED HOLE.
DUMP IT!
[both applause]
YAY!
- AH, WHAT THE [bleep]?
- ANDY?
- I'M OKAY.
- AH!
- OH, GOD.
- OH, MY GOD.
[heart monitor ringing]
- WELL, THAT BEEPING
WAS SURE ANNOYING,
BUT THIS IS
EVEN MORE ANNOYING.
- I'LL HANDLE THIS.
- THE MONITOR
IS NOT A TOY, ANDY.
- ANYTHING IS A TOY
IF YOU PLAY WITH IT.
- CHALK THAT UP
TO YOUR CONCUSSION.
WELL, THE GOOD NEWS
IS YOUR CAT SCAN'S CLEAR.
- COOL.
- ANDY, I'M REALLY HAPPY
YOU'RE OKAY.
LESLIE WAS WORRIED TOO.
WE SHOULD'VE CHECKED BEFORE
TO SEE IF YOU WERE...HOME.
- OH, NO, I TOLD YOU,
I MOVED OUT OF THE PIT.
I JUST HAD TO GO BACK
'CAUSE I FORGOT MY HEADPHONES.
AND I LAYED DOWN ON
THIS REALLY COMFY TARP
I SAW AN OLD CEREAL BOX
I HADN'T READ BEFORE,
SO I MUST'VE DRIFTED OFF.
NEXT THING YOU KNOW...
[explosive noise]
SWISHHHHH.
DIRT.
- SCOOT UP FOR ONE SEC.
AND BACK DOWN.
THERE YOU GO.
- [sigh]
THAT IS PERFECT.
IT'S LIKE
I'M LYING ON A CLOUD.
THIS IS AWESOME.
ANN AND ANDY,
JUST LIKE OLD TIMES.
THE PIT WORKS
IN MYSTERIOUS WAYS.
- I'M SORRY ABOUT ANDY, BUT
I'M NOT SORRY ABOUT WHAT I DID.
WHAT'S MY CRIME?
I GOT BOLD?
AND A LITTLE NEGLIGENT?
- KNOPE!
MY OFFICE, NOW!
- HEY.
CAN I SMOKE IN HERE?
- YOU DON'T SMOKE.
- JUST ASKING IF I CAN.
- ARE YOU HIGH?
- I'M HIGH ON KABOOM!
DON'T ASK FOR PERMISSION,
ASK FOR FORGIVENESS.
- THAT'S RIGHT, YOU NEVER DID
ASK ME FOR PERMISSION, DID YOU?
WELL, I'M SORRY
TO BURST YOUR KA-BUBBLE,
BUT I JUST HAD MY ASS KA-HANDED
TO ME BY THE CITY MANAGER,
AND NOW THIS ENTIRE
DEPARTMENT IS KA-SCREWED.
- RON,
I'M SO, SO, SO SORRY.
- WHAT THE KA-[bleep]
WERE YOU THINKING?
I WOULD PREFER THAT
SHE ASK ME FOR MY PERMISSION
SO I CAN SAY NO.
I LIKE SAYING NO.
IT LOWERS THEIR ENTHUSIASM.
- SO I BROUGHT YOU
SOME CLEAN CLOTHES
THAT I FOUND AT MY HOUSE.
- OH, MY GOD, MY SEXY SWEATER!
IT HAS A HOLE
CUT OUT OVER THE BICEP.
THANK YOU.
- NO PROBLEM.
- NO, A-CAKES, SERIOUSLY.
THANK YOU.
- YOU'RE WELCOME.
- NO.
THANK YOU.
- NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
WHAT DO YOU--WHAT DO YOU
THINK IS HAPPENING RIGHT NOW?
- A TRAGIC ACCIDENT
REIGNITED FEELINGS
YOU THOUGHT WERE LONG DEAD AND
WE ARE FINALLY BACK TOGETHER.
- ANDY...
WE'RE NOT BACK TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW THAT
I'M KIND OF WITH MARK NOW.
- OH, GOD,
IS THAT STILL HAPPENING?
I DON'T GET IT.
WHAT DOES HE HAVE
THAT I DON'T HAVE?
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- YEAH.
- EVERYTHING.
HE HAS LITERALLY EVERYTHING
THAT YOU DON'T HAVE:
A JOB, A CAR,
A STEADY INCOME, AN ADDRESS,
A SECOND PAIR OF SHOES,
TABLE MANNERS,
THE ABILITY TO SAY
"TAMPON" WITHOUT GIGGLING.
MARK HAS HIS LIFE TOGETHER.
I'LL GET YOU
A DIFFERENT NURSE.
- IT'S AWFUL
WHAT HAPPENED TO ANDY.
BUT SOMETIMES
WHEN YOU MAKE AN OMELET,
YOU GOTTA BREAK A FEW EGGS.
WHAT'S THE ALTERNATIVE,
NO OMELETS AT ALL?
WHO WANTS TO LIVE IN
THAT KIND OF WORLD?
MAYBE BIRDS.
THEN ALL THEIR BABIES
WOULD LIVE.
- MS. KNOPE?
LISTEN.
HI, SCOTT BRADDOCK,
CITY ATTORNEY.
- HEY, SCOTT.
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT
YOU WERE FRIENDS WITH ANDY.
- I NEVER MET HIM.
WHAT I DO KNOW IS THAT HE COULD
SUE US AT THE DROP OF A HAT.
I MEAN, RIGHT NOW HE IS THE MOST
DANGEROUS MAN IN PAWNEE.
- IS THAT ALL
YOU LAWYERS THINK ABOUT?
LAWSUITS, AND LAWS,
AND LEGALESE?
- YES.
- WELL, YOU CAN RELAX.
ALL I'M GONNA DO
IS GO IN AND JUST SAY,
"WE'RE SO SORRY,
IT'S ENTIRELY OUR FAULT"--
- NO, NO, NO, NO,
YOU CAN'T SAY ANY OF THAT.
IT ADMITS LIABILITY.
YOU CAN'T SAY "I'M SORRY",
OR "I APOLOGIZE."
IT IMPLIES GUILT.
- THAT'S INSANE.
I HAVE TO APOLOGIZE.
ANDY WAS THE VICTIM--
- CAN'T SAY "VICTIM".
- OF AN EXTREMELY UNFORTUNATE--
- CAN'T SAY "UNFORTUNATE",
AND YOU CAN'T SAY "SITUATION".
- I CAN'T SAY
THE WORD "SITUATION"?
- NO, IT IMPLIES
THERE WAS A SITUATION.
- CAN I GIVE HIM THE PIG?
- YEAH, PIG'S FINE.
- HI, ANDY.
- HI, LESLIE.
- GOT THIS FOR YOU.
- AW.
- HOPE YOU SQUEAL BETTER.
- AH.
[pig snorts]
[laughing]
- [clears throat]
- THIS IS MY FRIEND, SCOTT.
- HI, SCOTT.
- MM-HMM.
- ANDY, I JUST WANTED TO SAY,
I AM SO, SO, SO--
- MM-MM-MM-MM-MM.
- FILLED WITH EMOTIONS.
AS ANY PERSON WOULD.
[mouthing] I'M SORRY.
I'M SO, SO SORRY.
- WHAT?
- NO MIMING.
- UH...
UH, YOU WERE IN THE PIT.
- WE'RE NOT
CONCEDING THAT POINT.
- YOU WERE IN A PLACE...
WE'RE BOTH HERE NOW.
THE GOVERNMENT--
- NO, NO!
NO.
UH, WE GOTTA GO.
- WHAT?
- LET'S GO.
- WHY?
- COME ON.
- WENDELL ADAMS.
I'M ANDREW'S ATTORNEY.
- ANDY, NO!
- IT'S MY ONLY OPTION--
- ANDY, STOP.
I'VE ADVISED MY CLIENT
NOT TO SPEAK WITH YOU.
HE'S SUING
THE CITY OF PAWNEE.
- ANDY, YOU'RE
SUING YOUR HOME TOWN?
- ANDY, NO.
- CAN WE JUST TALK ABOUT THIS?
- LESLIE, NO.
- THIS IS TERRIBLE.
- DON'T SAY "TERRIBLE".
DON'T LOOK BACK.
[pig snorting]
[phone ringing]
- HELLO!
- ANDY, IT'S LESLIE.
- HELLO?
- HELLO.
ANDY, IT'S LESLIE.
- PSYCH!
LEAVE A MESSAGE AFTER THE BEEP.
[beeps]
- ANDY, IT'S LESLIE.
LOOK, WHAT DID YOU MEAN WHEN
YOU SAID IT'S YOUR ONLY OPTION?
I THINK WE SHOULD TALK.
WITHOUT LAWYERS PRESENT.
IF YOU WANNA MEET, JUST PUT
A WHITE CHALK 'X' ON THE MAILBOX
ACROSS THE STREET
FROM CITY HALL.
OR CALL ME BACK--
JUST CALL ME BACK.
[beeps]
ANDY, WHY AREN'T YOU
RETURNING MY CALLS?
IS IT BECAUSE OF YOUR LAWYER?
IT'S BECAUSE OF YOUR LAWYER.
[beeps]
HEY, ANDY, IT'S YOUR AUNT.
YOUR MOM OR DAD'S SISTER.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO TELL YOU
THIS, BUT YOUR UNCLE HAS PASSED.
HE'S WITH JESUS NOW.
SO WE'RE HAVING A MEMORIAL
IN 30 MINUTES AT CITY HALL.
[beeps]
HEY, FREE GUITARS AT CITY HALL!
EVERYBODY RUN!
[beeps]
[robot voice]
BECAUSE OF A LOCAL DISASTER,
YOU, ANDY DWYER, MUST
GO TO THE EVACUATION CENTER
AT PAWNEE CITY HALL...
[sighs]
- HM, THAT WAS WEIRD.
- [gasps]
HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN THERE?
- [sighs] I PROMISE THAT ANDY
ISN'T SUING JUST FOR THE MONEY.
- LESLIE,
THE MAN LIVED IN A PIT.
OKAY, HE COULDN'T FIND A PLACE
TO LIVE ON THE EARTH'S SURFACE,
SO HE WENT UNDER THE GROUND.
YOU'RE DEALING WITH A GROWN MAN
WHO THINKS LIKE A GOFER.
- I FEEL LIKE IF
I COULD GET PAST THE LAWYERS,
AND FIND OUT
WHAT'S REALLY GOING ON,
I THINK I COULD GET HIM
TO DROP THE LAWSUIT.
- [Andy on phone]
ANN, IS THAT YOU?
- HEY. WE NEED TO TALK
SOMEWHERE PRIVATE.
[knocking]
- OH!
- BABY, I'M BACK.
- THANK YOU SO--
WHAH! AH!
- WHY ARE YOU NAKED?
- OH!
- WELL,
BECAUSE OF WHAT YOU SAID,
WE'RE GETTING BACK TOGETHER.
- NO, WE'RE NOT.
- YES, WE ARE.
YOU SHOULD'VE HEARD THE SUPER
SEXY STUFF SHE WAS SAYING TO ME.
- I SAID "HEY, ANDY, IT'S ANN,
CAN WE TALK AT MY HOUSE?"
- THAT'S NOT HOW YOU SAID IT,
YOU WERE LIKE, "HEY, ANDY, IT'S
ANN, CAN YOU TALK AT MY HOUSE?"
- MY GOD, YOU'RE SUCH A BABY.
UGH, LITERALLY.
BIG NAKED BABY,
PUT CLOTHES ON.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I SHOULD'VE SEEN THIS COMING.
- HAS HE
SHOWED UP NAKED BEFORE?
- OH, YEAH--ANNIVERSARIES,
BIRTHDAYS, HOLIDAYS.
GOOD LUCK.
- WHERE ARE YOU--
HEY, ANN--JUST--
- NONE OF YOUR CLOTHES FIT ME,
SO I'M PUTTING AN APRON
OVER THE FRONT STUFF.
IS SHE GONE?
- WHAT DID YOU MEAN WHEN YOU
SAID THIS WAS YOUR ONLY OPTION?
- WELL,
I'M COMPLETELY BROKE.
AND MY LAWYER SAID IT COULD BE
WORTH UPWARDS OF $100,000.
- I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
YOU'RE SUING JUST FOR THE MONEY.
- I WANT ANN BACK,
AND SHE SAID SHE REALLY NEEDS
A GUY WITH A LOT OF MONEY.
- THAT DOESN'T SOUND LIKE ANN.
- WELL, I CAN'T
REALLY DO HER VOICE.
BUT SHE SAID SHE LIKES MARK
BECAUSE HE'S A GROWN-UP
WITH A BANK ACCOUNT.
I PUT TWO AND TWO TOGETHER,
$100,000, I CAN
PROBABLY GET A BANK ACCOUNT.
- SOMETIMES I THINK
THE RIGHT THING TO DO
IS TO NOT TAKE SHORTCUTS.
I MEAN, LOOK, I TRIED
TO FILL IN THE PIT.
THAT DIDN'T WORK EITHER.
- FINE.
I'LL GET A JOB.
ANN WILL RESPECT THAT.
I CAN MAKE SIX BUCKS A DAY
PLAYING GUITAR IN THE STREET.
I CAN'T MAKE SIX BUCKS A DAY.
- WAIT A SECOND, I KNOW I JUST
SAID THAT SHORTCUTS ARE BAD,
BUT I KIND OF JUST THOUGHT
OF AN AWESOME SHORTCUT.
- MR. DWYER, WE'RE VERY HAPPY
THAT YOU'RE DROPPING THE SUIT.
- YEAH,
IT'S REALLY TERRIFIC.
- I HAVE MY CONDITIONS.
- NO.
NEVER, I WILL NOT NEGOTIATE
WITH GREEDY STREET PEOPLE.
- WAIT, LESLIE,
LET'S HEAR HIM OUT.
- WE PLANNED THIS.
- CHUK-CHUK...KABOOM!
- ALL RIGHT,
WHAT'S IT GONNA TAKE?
- ONE, I WANT
THAT PIT FILLED IN, SIR.
- IS THERE A TWO?
- A GUARANTEED STARTING SPOT
ON THE INDIANAPOLIS COLTS--
INSIDE LINEBACKER.
- WE CAN'T ACCOMPLISH THAT.
- I THINK THAT ANDY
SEEMS LIKE HE DOESN'T
CARE SO MUCH
ABOUT THE SECOND ONE.
AND HE WOULD BE FINE
WITH US JUST FILLING IN THE PIT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY, SCOTT?
- YEAH.
EVENTUALLY, WE'RE
GONNA FILL IN THE PIT.
- EVENTUALLY?
I'VE ALREADY BEEN
INJURED IN THAT THING TWICE.
AND I CAN FALL IN TEN
MORE TIMES BY "EVENTUALLY".
EVERY TIME
I WALK PAST THAT PIT,
I'M FORCED TO RELIVE
THE MOST TRAUMATIC
TWO SEPARATE DAYS OF MY LIFE
AND WANNA SUE YOU AGAIN.
- WELL, I HATE TO SAY IT,
BUT IT REALLY SEEMS LIKE
ANDY HAS US
OVER A BARREL HERE, SCOTT.
- YEAH.
- THIS IS REALLY HAPPENING.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
- [laughing]
- OW!
- OH, SORRY.
USUALLY IN THESE SITUATIONS
A PERSON SAYS "PINCH ME."
- IS THAT ANDY?
- HUH, YEAH.
JUST ONE OF HIS CONDITIONS
FOR THE SETTLEMENT, I GUESS.
- HE SETTLED?
- YEP, GAVE UP
$100,000 PROBABLY.
JUST FOR ONE THING.
THE CITY FILL IN THE PIT
BEHIND YOUR HOUSE.
- WHY?
- WHO KNOWS?
WHO KNOWS WHY THAT GOPHER
DOES WHAT HE DOES?
- YOU ALWAYS
HATED THIS PIT!
- GOOD-BYE, PIT...
HELLO, LOT.
HOW DOES TAKING RISKS
MAKE ME FEEL?
AMAZING.
TINGLING SENSATION
THROUGHOUT MY WHOLE BODY.
I FEEL FLUSHED.
MY MUSCLES FEEL RELAXED,
YET I FEEL AWAKE.
JUST WAVES OF PLEASURE.
I WISH THERE
WAS SOMETHING PHYSICAL
THAT CAN MAKE ME
FEEL THIS WAY.
- WOW, YOU DID IT.
- YOU THINKING
WHAT I'M THINKING?
- THERE'S SO MUCH MORE TO DO.
- MY GOD, WE'RE SO CLOSE!
- YEAH.
- I'M GONNA CALL KABOOM!
AND CHECK ON THEIR
AVAILABILITY FOR NEXT YEAR.
- GREAT.
- [clears throat]
- [on phone]
INFORMATION.
- HI, YES, I'D LIKE
THE NUMBER FOR KABOOM!
THE NATIONAL PLAYGROUND
BUILDING CHARITY.
I HOPE THEY CAN WORK US IN.
- [woman on phone] I'M SORRY,
THERE'S NO LISTING.
- WHAT?
ARE YOU SURE?
- KABOOM! IS A WORD
I MADE UP.
IT'S NOT IN ANY DICTIONARY.
I TRICK PEOPLE
INTO BUILDING PLAYGROUNDS
IN EMPTY LOTS
IN THEIR NEIGHBORHOOD.
IT'S AN ELABORATE PRANK.
FOR MY NEXT PRANK,
I'M GOING TO BUILD A HOSPITAL
IN A POOR PART OF CHINA.
THEY'LL NEVER SEE IT COMING!
Captioning at CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com