- OKAY.
HERE'S THE SITUATION.
- YOUR PARENTS WENT AWAY
ON A WEEK'S VACATION.
THEY LEFT THE KEYS
TO THE BRAND NEW PORSCHE.
WOULD THEY MIND?
MM...
WELL, OF COURSE NOT.
* I'LL JUST TAKE IT
FOR A LITTLE SPIN *
[Haverford beatboxing]
* AND MAYBE SHOW IT OFF
TO A COUPLE OF FRIENDS *
* I'LL JUST CRUISE
AROUND THE NEIGHBORHOOD *
* WELL, MAYBE I SHOULDN'T--
YEAH, OF COURSE I SHOULD *
* PAY ATTENTION,
HERE'S THE THICK OF THE PLOT *
* PULLED UP TO THE CORNER
AT THE END OF MY BLOCK *
* THAT'S WHEN I SAW THIS
BEAUTIFUL GIRLY-GIRL WALKIN' *
* I PICKED UP MY CAR PHONE TO
PERPETRATE LIKE I WAS TALKIN' *
* THE SUNROOF WAS OPEN,
THE MUSIC WAS HIGH *
* AND THAT GIRL'S HAND WAS
STEADILY MOVING UP MY THIGH *
* SHE HAD OPENED UP THE BUTTONS
ON HER SHIRT SO FAR *
* I GUESS THAT'S WHY I DIDN'T
NOTICE THAT POLICE CAR *
* I CAN'T BELIEVE IT,
I MADE A MISTAKE *
* BUT PARENTS ARE THE SAME,
NO MATTER TIME NOR PLACE *
* SO TO ALL YOU KIDS
ALL ACROSS THE LAND *
* NO NEED TO ARGUE,
PARENTS JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND *
[cheers and applause]
THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
JUST A LITTLE
SOMETHING I KNOW.
SO WHAT'S UP?
- UH, SOMEONE IS ON FIRE
IN RAMSETT PARK.
THEY NEED YOU TO GET
DOWN THERE RIGHT AWAY.
- OH, MY GOD.
[triumphant music]
*
- I'VE BEEN SPENDING THE SUMMER
DOING A LOT OF ZOO PROMOTIONS.
* FOR HE'S
A JOLLY GOOD FELLOW... *
PARROTS LIVE
A VERY LONG TIME,
SO WE HAD A BIRTHDAY PARTY
FOR A PARROT THAT TURNED 60.
[everyone singing]
* WHICH NOBODY CAN DENY
[cheers and applause]
- YAY.
CHIMPANZEES ARE VERY SMART,
SO WE HAD THEM
GRADUATE FROM COLLEGE.
AND THEY LIKE
TO FLING THEIR FECES,
SO WE WERE HOPING THAT
THEY WOULD FLING THEIR HATS,
BUT THEY--
[gasps, splattering noise]
THEY JUST FLUNGTHEIR FECES.
[chimp screaming]
THE PAWNEE ZOO
RECENTLY PURCHASED
TWO SOUTH AFRICAN
BLACK-FOOTED PENGUINS,
TUX AND FLIPPER.
AND AS PART
OF OUR ZOO PROMOTION,
WE ARE GOING TO GIVE THEM
A MARRIAGE CEREMONY...
BECAUSE THEY MATE FOR LIFE.
TUX, DO YOU TAKE FLIPPER
TO BE YOUR LAWFULLY
WEDDED WIFE?
I DO. I DO.
BY THE POWER VESTED IN ME
FROM THE DEPARTMENT
OF PARKS AND RECREATION,
I NOW PRONOUNCE YOU
HUSBAND AND WIFE.
[cheers and applause]
[Mendelssohn's Wedding March]
[crowd giggling]
OH.
WELL...
[nervous giggle]
OKAY, WELL
AT LEAST THEY'RE MARRIED.
- ARE THEY MAKING BABIES?
- NO, NOT THOSE TWO.
THOSE ARE BOTH BOY PENGUINS.
- I'M SORRY?
- TUX AND FLIPPER
ARE BOTH BOYS.
SO YOU SHOULD HAVE
PRONOUNCED THEM
HUSBAND AND HUSBAND,
TECHNICALLY.
- THAT'S AWESOME.
[giggling]
- STILL...
YOU COULDN'T HAVE
ASKED FOR BETTER WEATHER.
[footsteps]
BRENDANAWICZ...
YOU BIG SANDWICH EATER.
- OH!
MM, CUT IT OUT NOW.
- [giggles]
OH, JUST TO BE CLEAR,
THAT WAS A FRIEND PUNCH.
THERE WAS NO, YOU KNOW,
FLIRTATIOUS MEANING
BEHIND THAT PLAYFUL PUNCH
I JUST GAVE YOUR ARM.
- YES, I DO UNDERSTAND.
UH, YOU'VE
MADE IT ABUNDANTLY CLEAR
THAT THERE'S NO ROMANTIC ELEMENT
TO OUR RELATIONSHIP IN ANY WAY.
- YES. GOOD.
ISN'T IT GOOD TO BE ABLE
TO JUST KIND OF
HORSE AROUND
LIKE THIS AS FRIENDS?
- IT IS...YEAH.
- YEAH.
- I REALLY HIT ROCK BOTTOM
THAT NIGHT.
AND I MEAN
THAT I LITERALLY FELL
TO THE BOTTOM OF
A PIT AND HIT A ROCK.
I REMEMBER LAYING THERE,
THINKING,
"THERE'S PROBABLY A GOOD
REASON WHY I'M DOWN HERE...
AND SINGLE."
[soft chuckle]
AND THEN I STARTED THINKING
THAT I NEED MORPHINE.
OH, YEAH. I HEAR YOU MADE TWO
MALE PENGUINS VERY HAPPY TODAY.
YOU'RE MAKING HISTORY, KNOPE.
I LIKE THAT,
STICKING YOUR NECK OUT.
- I--NO, I DIDN'T STICK
MY NECK OUT.
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
- OUT OF THE MAINSTREAM,
I THINK THAT'S COOL.
- I'M IN THE MAINSTREAM.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
- NO, NO, NOT OUT OF IT.
- SOCIAL ACTIVISM.
- NO. UH-UH.
PEOPLE IN THIS TOWN
DON'T REALLY LIKE
THEIR GOVERNMENT EMPLOYEES
BEING ACTIVISTS.
LAST YEAR, A GARBAGE MAN
WAS SUSPENDED
FOR WEARING
A LIVESTRONG BRACELET.
- HEY, LESLIE.
SOME GUY WHO OWNS A GAY BAR
SENT YOU A CAKE.
- PAWNEE HAS A GAY BAR?
- YEAH. THE BULGE.
IT'S BEHIND MY HOUSE.
- THE BULGE IS A GAY BAR?
[sighs]
THE NIGHTS I'VE WASTED THERE.
- "LESLIE, HEY GIRRRRRRRRL."
WITH EIGHT "R"s.
"THANK YOU FOR SUPPORTING
THE CAUSE OF GAY MARRIAGE.
YOU ROCK!
THE BOYS AT THE BULGE."
- THEY THOUGHT THAT
WAS A POLITICAL GESTURE?
OKAY, NOBODY EAT THAT CAKE.
TOM, STEP INTO MY OFFICE.
- THAT'S ALSO MY OFFICE.
- YEAH, WHATEVER.
I KNOW THAT YOU ARE NOT GAY.
- NO, I'M NOT.
- BUT YOU'RE EFFEMINATE.
- WHAT?
- WELL, YOU'RE WEARING A PEACH
SHIRT WITH A COILED SNAKE ON IT.
- YES, 'CAUSE IT WAS FEATURED
IN DETAILS MAGAZINE
AND IT'S AWESOME.
- EFFEMINATE.
ANYWAY,
SO THE POINT IS, DO YOU
THINK THAT MARRYING PENGUINS
MADE SOME KIND OF STATEMENT?
- YES, THE STATEMENT WAS
THAT YOU'RE VERY LONELY,
AND YOU NEED A PET.
- HUH.
- LESLIE, THEY SENT YOU
T-SHIRTS TOO.
- OH. WOW, LOOK
THEY SENT US A T-SHIRT.
HMM.
- MINE HAS A COLLAR ON IT.
- THERE SHE IS.
LESLIE!
- HEY.
THIS IS MY BOYFRIEND,
DEREK,
AND THIS IS
DEREK'S BOYFRIEND, BEN.
- HI.
- HEY.
OH!
WAIT, SORRY.
WHAT'S THE SITUATION?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- HOW DOES THIS WORK?
- DEREK IS GAY.
BUT HE'S STRAIGHT FOR ME,
BUT HE'S GAY FOR BEN,
AND BEN'S REALLY GAY
FOR DEREK.
AND I HATE BEN.
- IT'S NOT THAT COMPLICATED.
- NO.
- OH, YEAH.
SURE.
THE THING ABOUT YOUTH CULTURE
IS I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
SO WHAT CAN I DO
FOR YOU GUYS?
- THEY JUST REALLY
WANTED TO MEET YOU,
BECAUSE YOU'RE KINDA LIKE
THEIR HERO NOW.
- OH, OH, APRIL.
OH, PLEASE,
IT WAS JUST PENGUINS.
- NO.
- I'M A PUBLIC SERVANT,
AND I'M NOT ALLOWED
TO TAKE A POLITICAL STANCE.
- BUT YOU DID,
AND IT WAS AWESOME.
- YEAH, NONE OF THE OTHER
POLITICIANS EVER TAKE A STAND,
AND IT MEANS A LOT
TO THE WHOLE GAY COMMUNITY.
- OH, WELL...
- IT DOES.
AND WE'RE GONNA HAVE THIS PARTY
TOMORROW NIGHT AT THE BULGE,
AND WE HAD SOMETHING
TO ASK YOU.
WE REALLY WANT YOU
TO BE THE GUEST OF HONOR.
- OH, MY!
- IT'D BE AMAZING
IF YOU CAME.
- YEAH, YOU HAVE TO COME.
- WHO--WHO MADE THIS?
all: WE DID.
- HOW?
- PHOTOSHOP.
- WHAT?
- COMPUTERS.
- OH.
- HEY.
WHY ARE YOU ALL DOLLED UP?
- OH, IT'S A LONG STORY.
I'M THE GUEST OF HONOR
AT THIS GAY BAR TONIGHT.
I GUESS GAY MEN
ARE STARTING TO LIKE ME.
I DON'T KNOW, I GUESS THEY THINK
I'M FABULOUS OR SOMETHING.
- WELL, YOU LOOK GOOD, GIRL.
YOU GONNA
TURN SOMEBODY TONIGHT.
- [laughing]
THAT WAS, HANDS DOWN,
THE BEST INTERACTION
I'VE EVER HAD WITH DONNA.
- LESLIE,
THIS IS MARCIA LANGMAN
FROM THE SOCIETY FOR
FAMILY STABILITY FOUNDATION.
- OH, HELLO.
I LOVE YOUR TOP.
- OH, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I WAS JUST HOPING YOU
HAD A MOMENT TO DISCUSS
THE EVENTS
AT THE ZOO YESTERDAY.
- WELL, I HAVE NOTHING
TO DO WITH THIS, SO...
- WELL,
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU
AND THOSE FINE PEOPLE
AT THE SFSF?
- WELL, UM...
YOU COULD RESIGN.
[laughing]
IF YOU'RE UP FOR IT.
- OH, YOU'RE SERIOUS?
- WHEN YOU PERFORMED
A MARRIAGE FOR GAY PENGUINS
USING TAXPAYER MONEY
ON GOVERNMENT PROPERTY,
YOU WERE SYMBOLICALLY
TAKING A STAND
IN FAVOR OF
THE GAY MARRIAGE AGENDA.
- OH, I'M SORRY,
BUT HOLD ON A SECOND THERE.
MARCIA, THAT WAS
NOT MY INTENTION AT ALL.
- WELL, WHY ELSE
WOULD YOU MARRY PENGUINS?
- BECAUSE I FIRMLY BELIEVED
THAT IT WOULD BE CUTE.
AND IT WAS.
- LESLIE, ARE YOU MARRIED?
- NO.
UM, NOT YET, MARCIA.
SOON.
PROBABLY.
I HAVE A PLAN, BUT NOT--
NO, NOT NOW.
NOT DATING ANYONE YET.
FOCUSING ON MY CAREER,
BUT...
- I THOUGHT SO.
SO YOU COULDN'T
POSSIBLY UNDERSTAND.
BUT WHEN GAYS MARRY, IT RUINS
MARRIAGE FOR THE REST OF US.
SO EITHER
YOU ANNUL THE WEDDING
OR I'LL PUBLICLY
ASK FOR YOUR RESIGNATION.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M SO TERRIBLE WITH DIRECTIONS.
IF I'M HEADING
TO THE PARKING LOT,
DO I MAKE
A LEFT OUT OF HERE,
OR DO I GO RIGHT?
- IT'S A LEFT, YEAH.
- THANK YOU.
- YOU'RE WELCOME.
- ANNUL THE WEDDING!
- [exhales slowly]
- HEY.
- HI.
- I'M SUPPOSED
TO MEET LESLIE FOR LUNCH,
BUT SHE ACTUALLY WORKS, SO...
- OUCH.
- MARK WAS BROUGHT
TO MY HOSPITAL
THE NIGHT OF THE ACCIDENT.
HE WAS HERE FOR A WEEK.
I THINK WHEN
HIS HEAD HIT THE GROUND
IT MUST'VE
KNOCKED SOMETHING LOOSE,
BECAUSE HE'S ACTUALLY
A PRETTY NICE GUY NOW.
AND ANDY,
AFTER WE BROKE UP,
HE TOLD ME
HE WAS GOING TO KANSAS
TO CLIMB MOUNTAINS.
SO, I DON'T--I DON'T
REALLY KNOW WHERE HE IS.
- HEY, HAVE YOU SEEN
THAT DOCUMENTARY ABOUT FOOD YET?
- NO, I HAVEN'T.
BUT I HEARD IT'S REALLY GOOD.
I WANT TO SEE IT.
- WE SHOULD GO TOGETHER.
- WHAT?
OH, YEAH--NO.
I DON'T--
I DON'T THINK SO.
THAT--THAT WOULD BE
LIKE A--A DATE.
- OH, OKAY.
SAY NO MORE.
- MMM.
I HATE SALAD.
- LESLIE, I DON'T WANT
TO EVER KEEP SECRETS FROM YOU.
- OH, ME NEITHER.
LOOK, LET'S INVENT
OUR OWN SECRET LANGUAGE
THAT ONLY WE UNDERSTAND,
AND THEN WE CAN
USE IT AROUND PEOPLE
AND NO ONE WILL KNOW
WHAT WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- OKAY.
- BUT IN THE MEANTIME, I'M
JUST GONNA TELL YOU IN ENGLISH,
UH, MARK KIND OF
ASKED ME OUT.
HE WEIRDLY ASKED ME
TO GO SEE A MOVIE WITH HIM.
AND I SAID NO, OF COURSE.
BUT I JUST--I JUST
WANTED TO LET YOU KNOW.
- I'M FEELING A LOT OF
CONFUSING THINGS RIGHT NOW.
- YEAH--
NO, OF COURSE YOU ARE.
AND YOUR FRIENDSHIP IS
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING TO ME.
AND HE'S OFF-LIMITS.
- THANK YOU, MAN.
I JUST WANT YOU
TO KNOW I WAS REALLY SERIOUS
ABOUT THAT SECRET LANGUAGE.
- I KNOW.
[loud club music]
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS A GAY BAR.
- YEAH, ESPECIALLY
WITH THAT HETEROSEXUAL COWBOY
GREETING US ON THE WAY IN.
- WHERE SHOULD I DRINK NOW?
- THERE'S A BAR ON EIGHTH STREET
CALLED PITCHERS AND CATCHERS.
YOU CAN GO THERE.
- YEAH. HEY!
HEY, LISTEN,
HERE'S THE PLAN.
OUR POSITION IS
WE HAVE NO POSITION.
SO LET'S JUST SAY
THANK YOU FOR THE PARTY,
BUT WE REGRETFULLY DECLINE
YOUR OFFER TO HONOR ME.
- OH, MY GOD!
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU CAME.
- OH, HI, APRIL.
- DEREK, IT'S LESLIE KNOPE!
- LESLIE KNOPE,
YOU'RE MY HERO.
- OH, NICE.
- LESLIE...
YOU ARE LOOKING HOT.
- REALLY?
AW, THANK YOU, BEN!
AW, I'M REALLY
ENJOYING THIS HUG.
IT'S SO NICE, BUT I NEED
TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
- THIS ONE IS ON US.
- WELL, IF IT'S FREE.
- LESLIE KNOPE!
[cheers and applause]
- SHE--SHE'S LESLIE KNOPE
AND SHE WANTS TO RECRUIT YOU.
[cheers and applause]
- NO, NO, NO, NO.
OH, MY. OKAY, PLEASE--
[cheers and applause]
GENTLEMEN, FIRST OF ALL
I WOULD JUST LIKE
TO SAY THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR THROWING ME THIS PARTY.
ESPECIALLY ON A NIGHT
WHEN THE COLTS ARE PLAYING.
- WE LOVE YOU, LESLIE!
[cheers]
- OKAY.
HUH, THIS IS GREEN.
HMM.
[cheers and applause]
all: [chanting]
LESLIE, LESLIE, LESLIE!
LESLIE, LESLIE--
- OKAY.
WELL, I WANTED TO TELL YOU
THAT I WASN'T REALLY
TRYING TO TAKE A STAND
WHEN I MARRIED THOSE...
PENGUINS.
- LESLIE, LESLIE, LESLIE!
LESLIE, LESLIE, LESLIE!
- YOU'RE CHANTING MY NAME.
- LESLIE, LESLIE, LESLIE!
LESLIE, LESLIE, LESLIE!
- I JUST HAVE ONE THING TO SAY.
TOGETHER WE CAN
CHANGE PAWNEE FOREVER!
LET'S DANCE!
[cheers]
[cheers and applause]
- LESLIE KNOPE'S
IN THE BUILDING, Y'ALL.
LET'S GET WILD!
[hip-hop music starts]
*
- I'VE SEEN SO MANY DUDES
FROM CITY HALL HERE TONIGHT,
IT'S CRAZY.
BUT I GUESS
THEY'VE SEEN ME HERE TOO.
SO, UH, THAT'S NOT GREAT.
- HEY.
HI.
I GOT YOUR TEXT,
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
- OH, YEAH! THEY'RE
HAVING A PARTY IN MY HONOR.
GO TO THE BAR.
IF YOU'RE MY FRIEND,
YOU CAN DRINK FOR FREE.
- OH, COOL!
OKAY.
UH, AND MAYBE NEXT TIME,
DON'T USE THE WORDS
"MEDICAL EMERGENCY."
- I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE HERE!
- I'M REALLY SOBER.
- OKAY, I'LL GET
YOU A DRINK.
[mouthing lyrics]
- * BOOM BOOM
*
- YOU KNOW WHY
TONIGHT'S FUN?
'CAUSE EVERYONE'S SO GAY.
AND THEY KNOW
HOW TO HAVE FUN,
AND THE DANCING!
JUST...IT'S EVERYONE
IS JUST WHO THEY ARE,
AND WHO THEY ARE
IS JUST STONE-COLD GAY.
[Lady Gaga's Poker Face]
- * CAN'T READ MY
* CAN'T READ MY,
NO, HE CAN'T READ *
* MY POKER FACE
- * SHA BLAH BLAH
BLAH BLAH BLAH BLAH BLAH *
* MY MY MY MY POKER FACE
MY MY POKER FACE *
I'M HAVING SUCH
A NICE TIME TONIGHT.
I'VE MET
MANY INTERESTING PEOPLE.
AND THERE'S
TWO BISEXUAL GUYS HERE,
AND I GOT BOTH
OF THEIR PHONE NUMBERS.
HA HA!
* MY MY MY MY POKER FACE
MY MY POKER FACE *
* MY MY MY POKER FACE...
- ALL MORNING.
- * OH, OH, OH, OH, OH
* SHOW ME WHAT'S HOT,
SHOW ME WHAT I GOT *
* CAN'T READ MY,
CAN'T READ MY *
- HAVE FUN LAST NIGHT?
- I HAD THREE DRINKS
NAMED AFTER ME,
SO THAT'S PRETTY FUN.
PLUS, BEN AND DEREK ARE
TAKING ME SHOPPING ON SATURDAY.
AND WE ARE GONNA FIND OUT
MY ACTUAL BRA SIZE.
I GUESS I'M KIND
OF LIKE QUEEN OF THE GAYS.
- BULLY FOR YOU.
I JUST GOT A PHONE CALL.
THEY WANT YOU
TO GO ON PAWNEE TODAY.
- WOW, THAT'S HUGE!
WHAT'S THE TOPIC?
- YOU.
THAT MARCIA LANGMAN
FROM THE FAMILY THING
IS CALLING
FOR YOUR RESIGNATION.
- NO!
- YOU GOTTA GO ON
AND DEFEND YOURSELF.
- WHY?
I HAVEN'T EVEN OFFICIALLY
TAKEN A STAND ON GAY MARRIAGE.
- THAT'S FUNNY.
SOMEBODY JUST TOLD ME
YOU WERE QUEEN OF THE GAYS.
- THAT WAS ME.
- PAWNEE TODAY,
WITH JOAN CALLAMEZZO.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE THE
MEET THE PRESS OF OUR TOWN.
- IT'S THE BIG TIME, LESLIE.
- YEAH, I KNOW, IT IS.
I'M NERVOUS.
I JUST WISH I WAS HERE
UNDER DIFFERENT CIRCUMSTANCES.
[sighs]
- GUESS WHO!
- UM, MEGAN FOX?
- [laughing]
- ONE OF
THE DESPERATE HOUSEWIVES?
- [laughing]
NO, JOAN CALLAMEZZO.
- HEY, JOANIE!
WHAT'S UP, GORGEOUS?
GOOD TO SEE YOU!
- TOM COMES ON THE SHOW
ALL THE TIME; JOAN LOVES HIM.
- YOU HAVE THE SOFTEST SKIN
OF ANY WOMAN IN PAWNEE.
- THANK YOU.
- I WISH YOU COULD REACH
FROM YOUR TV SCREEN
AND JUST TOUCH JOAN'S SKIN
FOR A SECOND.
- OH, THAT'S SWEET.
- YOU'D HAVE A TREAT.
- YOU'RE PRETTY SOFT
YOURSELF.
- HOW ARE YOUR KIDS DOING?
- THEY'RE PRETTY GOOD.
- IS IT TOUGH FOR THEM TO HAVE
A MOTHER THAT IS SO BEAUTIFUL?
WHAT'S IT LIKE BEING THE
MOST ATTRACTIVE WOMAN IN PAWNEE?
- YOU KEEP UP THOSE FUNNIES.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO INVITE
YOU OVER FOR SUPPER.
- WELL, I'LL HAVE
TO COME OVER FOR SUPPER.
- OH! WELL...
- OH, MY GOD!
- ANN PERKINS.
HOW YOU DOING?
- [giggling]
I'M GOOD.
HOW WAS MOUNTAIN CLIMBING?
- OH!
WHAT?
- [awkward laugh]
- CAN I COME IN?
I JUST WANTED
TO TALK TO YOU FOR A SECOND.
- SURE, YEAH.
[generic Muzak]
- WE HAVE
A CONTROVERSIAL TOPIC TODAY--
THE GAY PENGUIN MARRIAGE
AT THE PAWNEE ZOO.
SO MARCIA,
WHAT IS ALL THE FUSS ABOUT?
- THE FUSS IS
THAT MISS KNOPE CLAIMED
THAT SHE WAS NOT
ADVOCATING FOR THIS GAY CAUSE.
AND THEN THAT VERY NIGHT,
SHE WAS THE GUEST OF HONOR
AT A PRO-GAY MARRIAGE RALLY
AT A BAR CALLED THE BULGE.
- MISS KNOPE,
HOW DO YOU RESPOND?
- I'D FIRST LIKE
TO SAY THAT I WASN'T
TRYING
TO ADVOCATE FOR ANYONE.
I DID NOT KNOW THAT BOTH
OF THE PENGUINS WERE MALES,
AND I WAS JUST TRYING
TO PERFORM A CUTE, FUN CEREMONY
TO PROMOTE OUR LOCAL ZOO.
- I HAVE TO SAY THAT
THAT STUNT THAT YOU DID
WITH THE PENGUINS
WAS CLEARLY OVER THE LINE.
NOW, MARCIA, WHAT--
IF ANYTHING--
CAN MISS KNOPE DO
TO MAKE IT RIGHT?
- UH, JOAN, WE DON'T
WANT TO BE UNREASONABLE.
- OF COURSE NOT.
- [laughing]
WE THINK THAT SHE
SHOULD SEPARATE THE PENGUINS,
ANNUL THE MARRIAGE,
REIMBURSE THE TAXPAYERS
FOR THE COST OF
THE WEDDING, OF COURSE,
AND THEN RESIGN.
- OH, IS THAT IT?
- THAT WOULD DO IT.
- ANYTHING ELSE?
WANT ME TO JUMP OFF A BUILDING?
PERFORM HARRY CARAY?
- MOVE TO A DIFFERENT TOWN.
NO, I KID.
- [nervous chuckle]
FULL OF IDEAS HERE TODAY.
- THIS IS THE REASON WHY
PEOPLE DON'T GO INTO POLITICS.
BECAUSE YOU KNOW, I BUST MY ASS
FOR THE PEOPLE IN THIS CITY,
AND I CAN'T WIN.
I HAVE ONE NIGHT OF FUN
WITH SOME OF THE BEST DANCERS
I'VE EVER DANCED WITH,
AND SUDDENLY
EVERYBODY'S FREAKING OUT?
- WOW, LOOK AT THAT!
WOW, WE'RE LIGHTING UP HERE.
- OH, GOOD.
GREAT, LET'S GO FOR IT.
OKAY, GREAT.
BRING IT ON.
HOW DOES THIS WORK?
- WELL, THERE,
YOU PRESS THAT ONE--
- GREAT, OKAY.
HEY, YOU'RE ON THE AIR.
- YEAH, I THINK
THAT LADY SHOULD RESIGN.
- OKAY, GOOD.
THANK YOU, NEXT CALLER.
- YOU SHOULD RESIGN
AND REPAY YOUR SALARY.
- OKAY, TWO FOR RESIGN.
THANK YOU, NEXT CALLER.
- I JUST WANT TO SAY
THAT I LOVE THE ZOO
AND THE ZOO IS REALLY FUN.
- THANK YOU.
THAT'S REALLY SWEET.
- AND I THINK
YOU SHOULD RESIGN.
- YOU LOOK GREAT.
YOU LOOK AMAZING.
- THANKS.
YOU LOOK FANCY.
- OH, YEAH.
THE MONKEY SUIT.
IT COST 3,000 BUCKS,
BUT TOTALLY WORTH IT.
I SOLD OUT.
[laughing]
I GOT A BORING
OFFICE JOB IN TOWN,
SO I GOTTA DRESS UP.
YOU KNOW, THE GRIND.
BUT I'M REALLY HAPPY,
AND I REALLY FEEL LIKE
I'VE MATURED...A LOT.
- GOOD, THAT'S--
I'M HAPPY FOR YOU.
- SO LISTEN, I WAS SITTING
IN THE CUBICLE THE OTHER DAY,
DOING SOME THINKING,
SOME GROWING...
- AND SOME MATURING.
- HA HA!
YES, MATURING.
AND DARN IT
IF I DON'T JUST MISS YOU.
- ANDY--
- AND--OH, "A"-CAKES,
JUST--
JUST LET ME, UH...
I LOVE YOU,
AND I'M JUST REALLY SORRY
FOR THE WAY THAT I TREATED YOU.
I WAS
THE WORST BOYFRIEND EVER.
I KNOW THAT.
AND I REALLY THINK
IT WOULD BEHOOVE US
TO GIVE IT ANOTHER SHOT.
- YEAH, LOOK...
I'M REALLY HAPPY
FOR YOU ABOUT YOUR JOB
AND THAT YOU'VE LEARNED
SOME NEW WORDS,
BUT I'M SURE
ABOUT MY DECISION.
- OKAY.
SAY NO MORE.
LISTEN, HIT ME UP
ON MY CELL PHONE.
I'LL BE AROUND.
AND IF YOU WANNA TALK
OR GRAB COFFEE,
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT, OKAY?
- OKAY.
- OH! GOTTA GET
BACK TO THE OFFICE.
[door opening]
HAVE A GOOD ONE.
- BYE.
- GOOD SEEING YOU.
[door closing]
THE HARDEST PART
ABOUT LIVING IN THIS PIT?
IT'S PROBABLY KEEPING
MY SUIT PRESSED.
AND THE RATS.
IT'S LIKE A FREAKIN'
RAT PARADE EVERY NIGHT.
I JUST WANT TO BE
CLOSE TO HER HOUSE
BECAUSE I NEED
TO PROTECT HER.
'CAUSE THERE ARE SOME WEIRD
PEOPLE THAT LIVE AROUND HERE.
- [on phone] YEAH, IF
YOU LET PENGUINS GET MARRIED,
WHERE DOES IT END?
I MEAN, WOULD YOU LET
ME MARRY MY GUINEA PIG?
BECAUSE I REALLY DO
WANT TO MARRY MY GUINEA PIG.
I'LL TAKE MY ANSWER
OFF THE AIR.
- I THINK
THAT'S A VALUABLE POINT.
- YOU KNOW, ATTENDANCE IS
UP 30% AT THE ZOO, BY THE WAY.
YOU'RE WELCOME!
AND THAT PENGUIN WEDDING
WAS CUTE, DAMN IT.
AND I'M NOT
GOING TO ANNUL IT.
- I'D ASK YOU TO RECONSIDER.
- WELL, I'D ASK
YOU TO STOP ASKING ME.
BECAUSE IT'S
NOT GONNA HAPPEN, MARCIA.
- IS THAT RIGHT?
- LAST TIME I CHECKED,
I DON'T THINK
I--I--I MURDERED ANYONE,
OR HAD AN AFFAIR,
OR DID DRUGS!
BUT I APOLOGIZE.
I APOLOGIZE FOR HAVING FUN
AND FOR MAKING SOMETHING CUTE.
- WHERE ARE YOU FROM
ORIGINALLY?
- OH, NO!
WHAT DID I DO?
- SO YOU WILL
NOT BE ANNULLING--
- NO,
I WILL NOT BE ANNULLING.
NO.
LOOK AT THEM.
THEY'RE JUST IN THEIR OWN
LITTLE...PENGUIN LOVE BUBBLE.
I GUESS THAT'S WHAT IT'S
LIKE WHEN YOU MEET YOUR MATE
AND KNOW YOU'RE
GONNA BE TOGETHER FOREVER.
[doorbell ringing]
- HI.
YOU KNOW WHAT I REALIZED?
- WHAT?
- WE'RE JUST ANIMALS.
WE DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT LOVE.
- OKAY.
- YEAH.
I THINK YOU SHOULD GO
ON THAT DATE WITH MARK.
- OH, LESLIE--
- REALLY, SERIOUSLY,
I THOUGHT ABOUT IT.
AND...LOOK, HE MIGHT NOT
BE MY GAY PENGUIN,
BUT HE COULD BE YOURS.
- LOOK, I TOLD YOU, I'M NOT
GOING ON A DATE WITH HIM.
- OKAY, FINE.
IF YOU DON'T WANNA GO OUT WITH
HIM, DON'T GO OUT WITH HIM.
BUT DON'T NOT
DO IT BECAUSE OF ME.
'CAUSE I'M REALLY FINE
WITH IT.
ALL THAT'S IMPORTANT TO ME
IS THAT WE'RE STILL FRIENDS.
- ME TOO.
- GOOD, GREAT.
PLUS, I ALREADY
CALLED AND TOLD HIM
THAT YOU WERE DYING TO GO OUT
WITH HIM, SO HAVE FUN.
- HUH?
- SO I TRANSFERRED
THE PENGUINS TO A ZOO IN IOWA.
GAY MARRIAGE IS LEGAL THERE,
SO HOPEFULLY
THEY'LL BE HAPPY.
AT LEAST
THEY'LL BE TOGETHER.
OH, LOOK!
SIX FLAGS!
I SHOULD TAKE THEM
ON A WATER SLIDE.
THEY MIGHT DIE.
BUT IT WOULD BE SO CUTE!
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com