- GOOD MORNING, EVERYONE.
COUPLE ANNOUNCEMENTS.
AS WE ALL KNOW,
RON IS RECOVERING
FROM HIS HERNIA SURGERY,
SO I GOT HIM FLOWERS
FROM ALL OF US.
SO EVERYBODY NEEDS TO PITCH IN,
LIKE, $90.
- $90?
- YES.
BECAUSE I ORDERED A BEAUTIFUL
BOUQUET OF DAFFODILS
FROM A WEBSITE
AFTER A FEW GLASSES
OF WINE.
SO, TOM, I THINK YOU MIGHT BE
GETTING SOME DAFFODILS TOO.
DONNA,
YOU'RE DEFINITELY GETTING SOME.
JERRY, I DON'T KNOW.
I'M NOT SURE.
TIME WILL TELL.
ALSO, I'M LEAVING EARLY TONIGHT
BECAUSE I AM A JUDGE
IN THE MISS PAWNEE
BEAUTY PAGEANT.
- WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, YOU GET
TO BE A JUDGE IN THAT THING?
- YES,
AND IT'S A RESPONSIBILITY
I TAKE VERY SERIOUSLY.
- BUT I WANT TO BE A JUDGE.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU LIKE BEAUTY PAGEANTS.
- APRIL, WHOEVER MISS PAWNEE IS,
IS GONNA BE THE REPRESENTATIVE
OF WOMANHOOD
IN OUR TOWN.
AND AS A JUDGE,
LET ME ASSURE YOU
THAT THIS YEAR'S MISS PAWNEE
WILL BE CHOSEN
FOR HER TALENT AND POISE.
- WHOA, THE GIRLS FROM TALENT
AND POISE ARE GONNA BE THERE?
- WHAT?
- TALENT AND POISE.
IT'S A STRIP CLUB
BY THE V.A. HOSPITAL.
I HAVE SOME MEETINGS THERE.
- UH, THAT'S DISGUSTING.
- NO, WHAT'S DISGUSTING
IS THE GLITTER FACTORY.
DO NOT GO
TO THE GLITTER FACTORY.
[triumphant music]
*
- HEY!
- HEY.
- SO I WAS JUST
AT THE GRIND,
AND I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT WANT
AN ICED MOCHA
WITH EXTRA, EXTRA
WHIPPED CREAM.
- OH, MY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, APRIL.
WOW.
- YOU'RE WELCOME.
OH, BY THE WAY,
COMPLETELY UNRELATED,
I JUST SIGNED UP FOR
THE MISS PAWNEE BEAUTY PAGEANT.
- THAT'S WONDERFUL.
YOU KNOW, THAT IS WHY
I DECIDED
TO BECOME A JUDGE.
SO THAT AWESOME GIRLS
LIKE YOU,
WHO ARE NOT, YOU KNOW,
CLASSICALLY HOT,
CAN BE REWARDED FOR THEIR
INTELLIGENCE AND SAVVY.
- BEAUTY PAGEANTS
ARE IDIOTIC,
BUT I FOUND THAT THE WINNER
OF THE MISS PAWNEE PAGEANT
GETS $600.
I CAN BE IDIOTIC
FOR $600.
SO ARE YOU GONNA VOTE
FOR ME, SISTER?
- APRIL, IT'S UNETHICAL FOR ME
TO SHOW YOU FAVORITISM.
YOU AND I
ARE LIKE FAMILY.
- THE COFFEE'S $7.
- YES, RIGHT, OF COURSE.
- JUST BUMP THAT CLOWN.
TELL HIM THEY ALREADY HAVE
ANOTHER ASIAN JUDGE.
AWESOME.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I OWE YOU.
A'IGHT, PEACE.
GUESS WHO'S ALSO GONNA BE
A JUDGE IN THE BEAUTY PAGEANT.
- WHAT?
HOW?
- I KNOW A GUY.
I HAD TO CALL IN
A FEW FAVORS.
BUT IF YOU DON'T CALL IN FAVORS
TO LOOK AT WOMEN IN BIKINIS
AND ASSIGN THEM
NUMERICAL GRADES,
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU
CALL IN FAVORS FOR?
- HEY.
- WHAT YOU DOING IN THESE PARTS?
- OH, I JUST--I CAME BY
TO SEE THE MURALS.
- OH.
- THIS ONE'S PRETTY AMAZING.
- YEAH, THIS ONE'S A BEAUTY.
YOU KNOW, IN THE 1880s,
THERE WERE A FEW YEARS
THAT WERE PRETTY ROUGH
AND TUMBLE IN PAWNEE.
THIS DEPICTS KIND OF
A FAMOUS FIGHT
BETWEEN REVEREND BRADLEY
AND ANNA BETH STEVENSON,
A WIDOWED MOTHER
OF SEVEN.
THE ORIGINAL TITLE OF THIS
WAS "A LIVELY FISTING."
BUT, YOU KNOW,
THEY HAD TO CHANGE IT.
FOR OBVIOUS REASONS.
- SHE'S GOT HIM BY THE HAIR
PRETTY GOOD THERE.
- YEAH.
- LESLIE'S REALLY COOL.
AND SHE'S SMART.
IT'S A LITTLE INTIMIDATING.
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
I DIDN'T COME HERE
TO LOOK AT THE MURALS.
I CAME TO ASK HER
ON A DATE.
HEY, LESLIE...
I REALLY--
I REALLY LIKE YOU.
AND I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU MAYBE WANT TO GET A CUP
OF COFFEE SOME TIME.
- OKAY. YEAH, SURE.
- YEAH?
- YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
LET ME CHECK
MY SCHEDULE.
- OKAY.
LET'S SEE...
- AH, IS THAT YOUR--
IS THAT YOUR GRANDMA?
- [laughs]
YEAH.
IT'S MADELEINE ALBRIGHT.
- THAT'S HER NAME?
I USUALLY JUST CALL MINE NANA.
- NO, THAT'S MADELEINE ALBRIGHT.
FIRST FEMALE SECRETARY
OF STATE.
- OKAY, SO NOT--
THAT'S NOT YOUR GRANDMA THEN.
ALL RIGHT.
I GOT IT.
HOW'S THAT SCHEDULE LOOKING?
- GOOD.
A COUPLE DAYS ARE FREE.
MAYBE WE COULD JUST,
YOU KNOW...
- LOCK IT IN LATER?
- YEAH.
- TALK LATER ABOUT IT?
- YEAH, THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
- OKAY.
LADIES.
- WANT TO HEAR SOMETHING AWFUL?
HE DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
WHO MADELEINE ALBRIGHT WAS.
- WHO?
- NOT YOU TOO.
MADELEINE ALBRIGHT,
FIRST FEMALE SECRETARY OF STATE.
- N-NO, WHO DIDN'T KNOW?
- OH, DAVE.
THAT COP THAT I MET.
I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN DATE SOMEONE
WHO DOESN'T SHARE
MY INTERESTS.
I MEAN, COULD YOU DATE
SOMEONE WHO DOESN'T
LOVE GIVING VACCINATIONS?
- I'VE NEVER DATED ANYONE
WHO LOVES GIVING VACCINATIONS.
[knock at door]
- HEY.
WEIRD QUESTION FOR YOU.
ARE YOU HANDY?
LIKE, CAN YOU FIX THINGS?
- WHAT'S BROKEN?
- MY SHOWER.
IT'S LEAKY, LOW PRESSURE,
JUST ALL AROUND TERRIBLE.
- UH, EASY.
YOU WANT ME TO COME OVER
AFTER WORK?
- YES!
YES, AMAZING.
I WILL COOK YOU
A CHEAP, QUICK DINNER
THAT WILL BE NO TROUBLE
AT ALL FOR ME.
- GREAT.
WELL, I'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT
FOR THE WEIRDEST SECOND DATE
EVER.
- OKAY.
- HELLO, FELLOW JUDGES.
I'M JUDGE LESLIE KNOPE,
AND THIS IS MY COLLEAGUE,
TOM HAVERFORD,
WHO'S ALSO GONNA BE A JUDGE.
- HI, JESSICA WICKS,
MISS PAWNEE 1994.
- I RECOGNIZED YOU
RIGHT AWAY.
AND MAY I SAY THAT YOU LOOK
EVEN MORE BEAUTIFUL NOW
THAN YOU DID
WHEN YOU WON THE CROWN.
- OOH, I LIKE YOU.
- RAY HOLSTEAD,
RAY'S SANDWICH PLACE.
- YES, OF COURSE, RAY.
HOW DO YOU DO?
- I'M CHARLES WOLINER.
I'VE JUDGED
EVERY MISS PAWNEE PAGEANT
FOR THE LAST 30 YEARS.
- WOW.
- I MADE JESSICA.
- HMM, WELL, TOM AND I
ARE VERY HAPPY TO BE HERE.
AND I'M SURE,
BETWEEN THE FIVE OF US,
WE WILL CHOOSE
THE MOST WELL-ROUNDED,
INTELLIGENT,
MODERN,
AND FORWARD-THINKING WOMAN
TO REPRESENT OUR FINE TOWN.
RIGHT, TOM?
- YOU DON'T BELIEVE ME?
WATCH.
34C, 36B,
34B, 34D.
32A?
HOW'D YOU GET IN HERE?
[laughter]
I'M JUST KIDDING.
YOU'RE PERFECT,
EACH AND EVERY ONE OF YOU.
GOD BLESS.
[applause]
- HERE THEY ARE,
YOUR CANDIDATES
FOR MISS PAWNEE.
[cheers and applause]
[pageant music]
*
LET'S MEET THE GIRLS,
SHALL WE?
FIRST UP, PLEASE WELCOME
APRIL LUDGATE.
[applause]
- HELLO, I'M APRIL LUDGATE.
I'M 20 YEARS OLD,
I LIKE PEOPLE,
PLACES,
AND THINGS.
AND PAWNEE IS MY FAVORITE PLACE
IN THE WORLD.
[applause]
- NEXT UP, PLEASE WELCOME
SUSAN GLEEVER.
- HI, EVERYONE,
I'M SUSAN.
I'M A HISTORY MAJOR
AT INDIANA STATE,
I PLAY CLASSICAL PIANO,
AND I VOLUNTEER
AT THE CHILDREN'S HOSPITAL.
[applause]
- THANK YOU, SUSAN.
- SHE'S GOOD.
- NEXT, TRISH IANETTA.
[cheers and applause]
- HI, Y'ALL.
I'M TRISH.
UM, I'M 22 YEARS OLD.
I'VE BEEN ON YOUTUBE.
I JUST LOVE
TO HANG OUT WITH MY FRIENDS.
I LOVE TO LAUGH.
I LOVE THE SUMMERTIME
AND GOING TO THE BEACH,
AND I LOVE WEARING BIKINIS
AT THE BEACH
WITH EVERYONE THERE...
- WELL, YOU KNOW,
THEY CAN'T ALL BE WINNERS.
- ARE Y'ALL HAVING
A GOOD TIME?
[cheers and applause]
- LOOKS LIKE WE GOT
A FRONTRUNNER, GUYS.
- AND NOW IT'S TIME FOR OUR
EVER-POPULAR TALENT COMPETITION
WHERE OUR LADIES
WILL EACH DEMONSTRATE
THEIR EXCELLENT SKILLS.
- HERE WE HAVE
LESLIE'S CUSTOM SCORE CARD
WITH CATEGORIES SUCH AS
PRESENTATION, INTELLIGENCE,
KNOWLEDGE OF "HERSTORY,"
FRUITFUL GESTURES,
JE NE SAIS QUOI,
AND SOMETHING CALLED
THE NAOMI WOLF FACTOR.
- AND OUR FIRST ONE UP
IS TRISH IANETTA,
WHOSE TALENT IS BATON.
[cheers and applause]
[hip-hop music]
*
- MY GIRL TRISH
IS TALENTED.
- SHE'S NOT EVEN TWIRLING
THE BATON.
- * WHEN YOU GO DOWN, DOWN
[microphone feedback]
- I'M GOING TO DO IMPRESSIONS.
- OH, CELEBRITY IMPRESSIONS.
THAT'S--THAT'S WILD.
WILD STUFF.
[laughter]
- YUP.
UM, THIS IS AN IMPRESSION
OF MY SISTER.
- HI, I'M NATALIE.
I LOVE RITALIN
AND HAVE LOW SELF-ESTEEM.
- [laughs]
- THANK YOU.
THIS IS AN IMPRESSION
OF MY BOSS,
LESLIE KNOPE.
WOMEN SHOULD DO EVERYTHING.
CHECK OUT MY FOUR-COLOR PEN.
HEY, EVERYBODY,
LISTEN UP WHILE I TALK
ABOUT SOME REALLY, REALLY,
REALLY IMPORTANT STUFF.
PARKS, PARKS, PARKS, PARKS,
PARKS, PARKS,
MICHELLE OBAMA, PARKS.
GAY PENGUINS, PARKS,
SUGAR, PARKS.
[laughter]
- SHE GOT ME.
SHE GOT ME GOOD.
- * OH
* IT'S SO GOOD,
IT'S SO GOOD *
* IT'S SO GOOD
[classical music]
*
- I'M TEXTING TRISH TO TELL HER
HOW GOOD SHE DID EARLIER.
- SHH.
- NO, SUSAN ISN'T A PERFECT 10.
BUT, IN MY MIND, SUSAN
IS THE PERFECT MISS PAWNEE.
HER VALUES ARE STRONG.
HER COMMITMENT TO HER JOB
IS VERY ADMIRABLE.
SHE HAS A REAL SENSE OF...
HEY.
OVER HERE.
- HOW'S IT GOING IN HERE?
- GOOD.
UM, I HOOKED YOUR TOILET
UP TO YOUR SHOWER.
THAT'S WHAT YOU WANTED,
RIGHT?
- YES.
- EXCELLENT.
- IS THAT ANDY?
ANDY?
I KNOW YOU'RE IN THERE
BECAUSE I CAN SEE YOU
THROUGH THE SCREEN.
- ANN.
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- DO YOU LIVE DOWN HERE?
- WHAT?
[laughs]
WHAT?
YES.
- OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD,
YOU LIVE DOWN HERE.
OH, MY GOD, I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS HAPPENING.
WHAT?
I CAN'T BE AT MY HOUSE
AND SEE MY EX-BOYFRIEND
LIVING IN A HOLE
IN MY BACKYARD
LIKE A GOPHER.
THAT'S SO WEIRD, ANDY.
- LISTEN, I HAVE BEEN TRYING
REALLY HARD
NOT TO BOTHER YOU.
LIKE, WHEN YOU HAD THAT BARBECUE
LAST WEEK,
I DIDN'T COME UP,
EVEN THOUGH IT SMELLED SO GOOD.
- YOU'VE BEEN HERE
A WHOLE WEEK?
- YES.
ONE WEEK ONLY.
- OH, I GUESS THAT'S THE OFFICE
THAT YOU WERE TELLING ME ABOUT
THAT YOU GO
TO WORK TO EVERY DAY.
EXCELLENT.
- LISTEN.
ARE WE GONNA TALK ABOUT ANYTHING
OTHER THAN THE LIES
THAT I TOLD YOU?
- OH, I CAN'T DO THIS
RIGHT NOW.
I HAVE A GUY
FIXING MY BATHROOM.
I GOT TO GO.
- YEAH, THAT'S COOL.
I GOT TO ZOOM OUT TOO.
'CAUSE I HAVE SOME PEOPLE
COMING OVER,
SO WHY DON'T YOU CALL FIRST
NEXT TIME?
YOU KNOW THE WAY OUT.
- [groans]
- ALL RIGHT, IT'S TIME NOW
FOR THE DREADED Q&A.
AND THE FIRST QUESTION GOES
TO TOM HAVERFORD.
- AH, YES, I HAVE A QUESTION
FOR THE HOT ONE.
FIRST OFF, I JUST WANT
TO SAY
I'M A LITTLE BIT SURPRISED
BECAUSE I DIDN'T THINK
ANGELS COULD FLY SO LOW.
- [laughs]
THANK YOU.
YOU TRULY ARE
A BEAUTIFUL, BEAUTIFUL WOMAN.
- [laughs]
YOU'RE SO FUNNY.
- YOU'RE FUNNY.
YOU'RE FUNNY.
- DO YOU HAVE A QUESTION,
TOM?
- OKAY, I, ACTUALLY,
I HAVE A REAL QUESTION.
IF YOU DON'T MIND, TOM.
TRISH, ALEXIS DE TOCQUEVILLE
CALLED AMERICA
THE GREAT EXPERIMENT.
WHAT CAN WE DO AS CITIZENS
TO IMPROVE ON THAT EXPERIMENT?
- UM, WELL...
I THINK THAT AMERICA
IS THE LAND
OF THE FREE,
WHICH IS A WONDERFUL THING,
AND ALSO THE BRAVE,
WHERE PEOPLE CAN LIVE.
AND NO ONE CAN EVER TAKE THAT
AWAY FROM YOU.
AND IT NEVER GIVES UP.
BUT THE HIGH BIRTHING RATE
OF IMMIGRANTS FRIGHTENS ME.
NO OFFENSE TO ANYONE OUT THERE,
BUT IF IT WERE UP TO ME
AND MY FAMILY,
I WOULD ACTUALLY CALL IT
OUR AMERICA
AND NOT THEIR AMERICA.
THANK YOU.
[applause]
- DON'T APPLAUD THAT.
DON'T--SHE DIDN'T ANSWER
MY QUESTION.
- I'M SORRY,
YOU DON'T THINK IT'S WEIRD
THAT MY EX-BOYFRIEND LIVES
IN A TENT
IN THE PIT
OUTSIDE MY HOUSE?
- IT'S NOT IDEAL.
UH, MAYBE YOU SHOULD TRY
TO RELAX.
MAYBE TAKE ONE OF THOSE ATAVINS
I SAW IN THE MEDICINE CABINET.
- DUDE.
- YEAH, I PEEKED.
I ALSO DIDN'T SEE
ANY TOOTHPASTE.
DO YOU NOT USE TOOTHPASTE?
- I MEAN, I ALWAYS KNEW
HE WAS LAZY,
BUT THIS IS LIKE A NEW LOW
FOR HIM.
[thunder crashes]
- I FEEL LIKE
WE SHOULD INVITE HIM INSIDE.
- HAVE YOU NOT BEEN LISTENING
TO ANYTHING I JUST SAID?
- I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S RAINING OUTSIDE.
AND HE'S LIVING IN A PIT,
YOU KNOW?
- [groans]
- OKAY, FOLKS,
JUST A COUPLE MORE CONTESTANTS,
AND THEN THE JUDGES WILL DECIDE
OUR NEXT MISS PAWNEE,
A WINNER OF $600
IN GIFT CERTIFICATES
TO BIG ARCHIE'S SPORTING GOODS
AND EMERSON FENCING COMPANY.
- WHAT?
WE DON'T GET CASH?
THIS IS FOR A FENCE?
- WELL, IT WON'T COVER
A WHOLE FENCE,
BUT IT WILL DEFRAY
THE COST CONSIDERABLY.
- OH, MY GOD.
I QUIT.
- OKAY.
I GUESS SHE REALLY IS QUITTING.
- NO, I DIDN'T WIN.
BUT AT LEAST I DIDN'T MAKE
ANY NEW FRIENDSHIPS.
- SO HOW LONG DO WE HAVE
TO PRETEND TO DELIBERATE
TILL WE GET BACK OUT THERE?
[laughter]
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- WE'RE ALL IN AGREEMENT.
THE HOT ONE,
BY A LANDSLIDE.
- WELL, HER NAME IS TRISH,
AND I DON'T THINK
WE SHOULD RUSH THIS, YOU KNOW.
- WHAT IS THERE
TO TALK ABOUT?
I MEAN, I THOUGHT
TRISH WAS JUST ADORABLE.
- WELL, TAKE SUSAN,
FOR EXAMPLE.
I THINK--
- SUSAN "BORING STORIES"? NAH.
IT'S TRISH.
LET'S GO BACK OUT THERE.
- OKAY, HOLD ON, EVERYONE.
HOLD ON.
EVERYONE, W-WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
LOOK, WHOEVER WE CHOOSE
IS GONNA REPRESENT
THE IDEAL WOMAN
FOR A YEAR.
SHE'LL BE SOMEONE
THAT LITTLE GIRLS
IN SOUTH-CENTRAL INDIANA
LOOK UP TO.
NOW NOBODY LEAVES THIS ROOM
UNTIL WE DISCUSS ALL OF IT,
OKAY?
CONSIDER YOURSELVES SEQUESTERED.
I'M A JUDGE,
SO I DON'T WANT
TO SOUND PARTIAL,
BUT TRISH WILL WIN THIS PAGEANT
OVER MY DEAD BODY.
- LOOK, I'M THE ONLY ONE HERE
WHO HAS ENTERED
AND WON THIS CONTEST
IN THE PAST.
AND I THINK TRISH
IS A NO-BRAINER.
- JESSICA, MAY I ASK,
WHAT WAS YOUR TALENT?
- OH, I PACKED A SUITCASE.
- I HAVE TO SAY,
LESLIE DOES MAKE
A GOOD POINT.
TRISH IS NOT THE BRIGHTEST BULB
IN THE BUNCH.
- YES, RAY, GOOD.
I LIKE WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
LET'S KEEP TALKING.
- JUST STAND OVER THERE,
AND DON'T DRIP ON ANYTHING.
- IS MARK THE GUY
WHO'S FIXING YOUR SHOWER?
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU,
MARK,
BUT I'VE SEEN
A TON OF PORN,
AND I KNOW WHAT FIXING
YOUR SHOWER MEANS.
- ANDY.
- SORRY, YOU GUYS
ARE ON A DATE.
THAT'S COOL.
- ANDY.
- NO, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
DON'T LET ME INTERRUPT
YOUR DATE.
- DIG IN.
- I ALREADY ATE.
I'M SUPER FULL.
I DON'T--
I DIDN'T WANT ANY.
- OKAY, SO IT'S STILL 3-2
FOR TRISH.
GUYS, ALL I ASK
IS THAT YOU LOOK
INTO YOUR HEARTS
AND THINK,
REALLY THINK,
ABOUT WHAT YOU'VE SEEN
AND ASK YOURSELVES,
WHO IS THE MOST IMPRESSIVE WOMAN
HERE TONIGHT?
- IT'S THE HOT ONE,
TRISH IANETTA.
[pageant music]
*
- THESE ARE AMAZING.
DO YOU--DO YOU PUT A LOT
OF HOT SAUCE
ON THESE OR SOMETHING?
- A GOOD CHEF NEVER REVEALS
HER SECRETS.
- IT'S HOT SAUCE.
ANN IS AN EXTRAORDINARY COOK.
MM.
MEMORIES.
- DO YOU WANT SOME MORE?
ARE YOU HUNGRY STILL?
- YOU KNOW WHAT'S FUNNY?
I WAS JUST SITTING OVER HERE
ON THE COUCH,
AND I WAS THINKING
THAT THERE WAS ONCE A TIME
WHEN MARK USED TO BE
THE STRANGER IN THE HOUSE.
AND NOW IT'S ME.
- EXCUSE ME, EVERYONE.
UM, WHY DON'T WE JUST TAKE
A MOMENT TO GIVE A ROUND
OF APPLAUSE TO ALL
THE CONTESTANTS THIS EVENING?
YES.
[applause]
ESPECIALLY SUSAN.
THIS ISN'T THE FIRST TIME THAT
SUSANS HAVE LOST TO TRISHES.
AND IT WON'T BE THE LAST.
SUSAN AND I WILL CONTINUE ON
UNTIL THE WOMEN OF PAWNEE
ARE JUDGED
NOT BY THE FLATNESS
OF THEIR TUMMIES,
BUT BY THE CONTENTS
OF THEIR BRAINS.
AND, TRISH,
I MAY NOT HAVE VOTED
FOR YOU,
BUT NOW IS A TIME
FOR US TO COME TOGETHER.
I HOPE YOU HONOR
THIS CROWN WITH DIGNITY
AND A DEVOTION TO--
- WHOO!
all: ONE, TWO, THREE.
[laughter]
- AS USUAL, ANN,
DELICIOUS MEAL.
ARE WE DOING ANYTHING IN THE WAY
OF DESSERT OR COFFEE?
- WE ARE LEAVING.
- OKAY, I GET IT.
DON'T WORRY. I'M VERY GOOD
AT PICKING UP SIGNALS.
LET'S GO, MARK.
- NO, DUMMY,
JUST YOU.
- OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
- TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
- JUST DON'T WORRY
ABOUT ME, ANN.
OKAY?
I'LL BE FINE.
THAT WENT REALLY WELL!
WE HAD DINNER,
I GOT TO SEE HER.
OH, GOD, I WAS SO TEMPTED
TO LOOK BACK AT HER.
WAS SHE LOOKING?
I HAD TO WALK SO SLOW.
AGH.
A GOOD DAY.
- WELL, WELL, WELL,
LOOK WHO'S HERE.
IT'S OFFICER JOHN MCCLANE.
WELCOME TO THE PARTY,
PAL.
- WHO'S THAT?
- DIE HARD.
- BATTERY?
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- WELL, YOU KNOW, THE OTHER DAY
I ASKED YOU
IF YOU WANTED
TO HAVE COFFEE?
- YEAH.
- YOU SAID YES.
- YES.
- OKAY.
AND THEN AFTERWARDS,
I SAW YOU AGAIN,
YOU KIND OF ACTED
LIKE YOU DIDN'T WANT
TO HAVE COFFEE ANYMORE.
WE LEFT IT KIND OF OPEN-ENDED.
- WE DID.
- AND THAT'S MADE ME
UNCOMFORTABLE.
- OKAY.
- SO I THOUGHT I'D COME IN
AND ASK YOU.
JUST GET SOME CLEARANCE
ON THIS.
- DAVE, I LIKE YOU.
- I LIKE YOU TOO.
OKAY, SO,
WE'LL GET COFFEE THEN.
- BUT I'M JUST BUSY.
RIGHT NOW,
MY SCHEDULE'S JUST SO...
- OKAY.
OKAY, I GET IT.
LOOK, I'M NOT A GUY
WHO PLAYS GAMES.
OKAY, I JUST CAME TO TELL YOU
THAT I LIKE YOU,
AND I LIKE COFFEE,
AND IF YOU WANT TO GET
SOME COFFEE, JUST...
HERE'S MY NUMBER.
COMING THROUGH,
BUDDY.
HEY, I GOT YOUR MESSAGE.
- HEY.
THANKS FOR COMING.
LOOK, I'D LOVE
TO GO OUT WITH YOU.
HOW ABOUT FRIDAY
FOR DINNER?
- YEAH?
GREAT.
HEY, UM, WILL SANDRA DAY
O'CONNOR AND MICHELLE OBAMA
AND CONDOLEEZZA RICE
AND NANCY PELOSI--
ARE THEY GONNA JOIN US?
- NO, THEY WILL
NOT BE JOINING US.
- OKAY, WELL, GOOD, 'CAUSE
I DON'T HAPPEN TO AGREE
WITH MISS PELOSI'S VIEWS
ABOUT THE TROUBLED ASSETS RELIEF
PROGRAM.
- HMM.
- I LOOKED THAT UP
TO IMPRESS YOU.
- I FIGURED.
- YEAH.
- IF YOU GUYS LIKE GRILLING,
YOU WANT TO COME OVER,
USE MY GRILL,
LET ME DO YOU A FAVOR.
TAKE A KEY,
JUST COME BY,
GRILL UP WHATEVER YOU WANT.
THIS IS ONE OF MY FAVORITE
PICK-UP STRATEGIES.
I'M CONSTANTLY GIVING WOMEN
MY KEYS.
- THIS IS YOUR HOUSE KEY?
- YEAH, YEAH, I JUST HAPPEN
TO HAVE A SPARE.
JUST COME BY, GO FOR A DIP
WHENEVER YOU WANT.
SO FAR,
NONE OF 'EM HAVE SHOWN UP.
- THAT'S A VERY APPEALING OFFER.
THANK YOU.
- MATTER OF TIME.
HEY, CRAIG.
- HEY, TOMMY.
- 50 MORE COPIES,
PLEASE.
- YOU GOT IT.
- I HAVE BEEN ROBBED TWICE.