- OKAY, AS EVERYBODY KNOWS,
THE SPIRIT OF PAWNEE
WAS DEFACED AGAIN LAST NIGHT.
- WHAT WAS IT THIS TIME?
- CHOCOLATE PUDDING.
- HUH. THAT'S NEW.
THE MURAL THAT NORMALLY
RESIDES HERE
IS CALLED
THE SPIRIT OF PAWNEE,
AND IT'S VERY CONTROVERSIAL.
WE'VE HAD SOMEONE
THROW ACID AT IT, TOMATO SAUCE.
SOMEONE
TRIED TO STAB IT ONCE.
WE REALLY NEED
BETTER SECURITY HERE.
WE ALSO NEED...
BETTER, LESS-OFFENSIVE HISTORY.
- SO THE CITY COUNCIL
HAS DECIDED
THAT THE SPIRIT OF PAWNEE
SHOULD BE CHANGED
TO SOMETHING JUST
A LITTLE LESS HORRIFYING.
NOW SINCE THE MURALS WERE MADE
BY GOVERNMENT EMPLOYEES
BACK IN THE 1930s,
WE THOUGHT IT MIGHT BE FUN
IF EACH DEPARTMENT
SUBMITTED THE DESIGN
FOR A NEW MURAL...
AND YOU'LL SUBMIT YOUR CONCEPTS
TOMORROW AFTERNOON.
ALL RIGHTY, FOLKS?
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
- UH, LESLIE, WHAT'S YOUR
DESIGN GONNA BE?
A TREE?
- JOE, YOU WORK IN SEWAGE.
YOUR DEPARTMENT LITERALLY
SPECIALIZES IN CRAP.
YOU REALLY WANNA DO THIS?
- I TOLD YOU BEFORE.
CRAP IS A SLANG TERM,
AND I DON'T LIKE THAT TERM.
BUT AT LEAST WE DON'T SPECIALIZE
IN LOSING...LIKE YOU GUYS.
SEWAGE, LET'S ROLL.
- DAMN!
HOW DOES SEWAGE ALWAYS GET
THE HOTTEST INTERNS?
[optimistic music]
*
- GUYS, THIS DEPARTMENT
HAS THE CHANCE
TO DESIGN SOMETHING THAT COULD
BE IN THIS BUILDING FOREVER.
THIS COULD BE OUR LEGACY.
- I THOUGHT BUILDING A PARK
ON LOT 48
WAS GONNA BE OUR LEGACY.
- WELL, YOU CAN HAVE
TWO LEGACIES.
LOOK AT MADONNA--
GREAT SINGER, AMAZING ARMS.
- LOOK AT O.J. SIMPSON--
HEISMAN TROPHY WINNER,
NAKED GUN.
- MM-HMM.
- NO OFFENSE, LESLIE,
BUT I'M NOT AN ARTIST.
- OH, THAT'S NOT TRUE, DONNA.
I'VE SEEN YOUR FINGERNAILS.
- I PAY SOMEONE TO DO THIS.
- REALLY? OH. WELL...
SHOOT.
ANYWAY...
I'M ORDERING ALL OF YOU
TO DESIGN A MURAL.
- AH...ONLY RON CAN ORDER
THE WHOLE DEPARTMENT
TO DO SOMETHING.
- RON, ORDER THEM TO DO THIS.
- DO WHATEVER LESLIE SAYS.
- HA HA! OKAY.
SO HERE ARE YOUR SUPPLIES.
I WANT YOU TO GO AND FIND
THE SPIRIT OF PAWNEE
AND MAKE ME A SKETCH.
AND IT NEEDS TO BE BREATHTAKING
AND MOVING AND HISTORICAL
AND BETTER
THAN EVERY DEPARTMENT,
AND YOU HAVE ONE HOUR.
[drawling voice]
DESIGNERS, MAKE IT WORK.
TIM GUNN.
- YOU, MY FRIEND,
ARE READY TO GO DANCING.
THANK YOU, SIR.
ALL RIGHT, NEXT.
[snaps]
- ANDREW, LOOKING GOOD.
BUSINESS IS BOOMING.
- YEAH. HEY, RON,
HOW ABOUT YOU?
NEED A LITTLE DOG WAXIN'?
IT'S ONLY 5 BUCKS, AND I'LL LET
YOU CUT IN FRONT OF THIS GUY.
- WHAT?
- COME ON, BEAT IT.
THIS IS RON SWANSON
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- I'M IMPRESSED WITH ANDY.
PULLING HIMSELF UP
BY HIS BOOTSTRAPS.
REMINDS ME OF ME.
I GOT MY FIRST JOB
WHEN I WAS NINE.
WORKED AT A SHEET METAL
FACTORY.
IN TWO WEEKS,
I WAS RUNNING THE FLOOR.
CHILD LABOR LAWS
ARE RUINING THIS COUNTRY.
- DO YOU HAVE A KEY
IN YOUR SHOE?
- NO, NO, I HAVE A BUNION
THAT'S PRACTICALLY ITS OWN TOE.
NORMALLY, THE PAIN
HOWLS THROUGH MY LOAFERS
LIKE A BANSHEE ON THE MOORS,
BUT...FOR THESE
PAST THREE MINUTES,
IT'S BEEN REDUCED
TO A FAINT GROWL.
- OKAY.
THAT WAS NEAT.
WELL, HEY.
WE ARE ALL FINISHED.
- WELL...[grunts]
WHOO.
THAT WAS GREAT.
- THANK YOU, SON.
- NO SWEAT!
NEXT!
- SHOULDN'T LET YOUR FRIENDS
CUT IN LINE.
IT'S NOT GOOD BUSINESS.
- YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE
ISN'T GOOD BUSINESS?
THAT GUY'S MY FRIEND.
- RIGHT.
I'M SAYING...
YOU SHOULDN'T
LET YOUR FRIENDS CUT IN LINE.
- ALL RIGHT.
SORRY, KYLE.
HERE, GIVE ME THIS.
NEXT!
- SO WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING
FOR EXACTLY?
- I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
THE SPIRIT OF PAWNEE.
THAT'S ALL I GOT.
HERE. JUST GIMME
$20 WORTH OF ART.
JUST SOMETHING
THAT SEEMS PERSONAL
THAT ONLY I COULD HAVE DONE.
- WELL, TELL ME ABOUT YOURSELF.
- NO. JUST PAINT.
I HAVE NO INTEREST IN ART.
LET ME CLARIFY.
I HAVE NO INTEREST
IN NON-NUDE IMAGES.
DUDE, WHAT THE HELL
KIND OF ART IS THIS?
LOOKS LIKE A LIZARD
PUKING UP SKITTLES!
- I'M AN ABSTRACT EXPRESSIONIST.
- NO, YOU'RE A CON ARTIST,
AND I'M A GUY
THAT'S OUT 20 BUCKS.
UGH. WHATEVER.
- I'M A TERRIBLE ARTIST.
BUT THE PARKS DEPARTMENT
HAS DONE SO MUCH FOR ME
THAT IF I CAN HELP THEM OUT
IN ANY WAY, I WILL.
OH, GOD.
MAYBE I SHOULD JUST GIVE THEM
ALL FREE FLU SHOTS.
- I KNOW EVERYTHING
ABOUT THIS TOWN
AND THESE MURALS,
AND THAT'S WHY THIS IS
A DREAM COME TRUE--LITERALLY.
I HAVE HAD A DREAM
WHERE I DESIGNED A MURAL.
BUT THEN IT TURNED INTO
A NIGHTMARE
BECAUSE THE MURAL
STARTED TALKING,
AND IT CAME ALIVE,
AND IT WAS WHISPERING,
AND I COULDN'T HEAR
WHAT IT WAS SAYING,
SO I LEANED IN CLOSE,
AND THEN IT ATE ME.
AT ONE POINT,
GINA GERSHON WAS THERE.
- MY PIECE
IS TRULY GOING TO CAPTURE
THE SPIRIT OF PAWNEE.
EEW!
- NEVER UNDERSTOOD
THE TERM ELBOW GREASE.
I GUESS
IT'S NOT REALLY GREASE.
JUST HARD WORK.
OH, HEY, RON.
NICE SHINY SHOES YOU GOT THERE.
- OH, HEY, I WAS JUST, UM...
OH, NO--SHOOT.
ACTUALLY, IT LOOKS LIKE
I SCUFFED THIS ONE.
- DO YOU NEED YOUR MONEY
BACK, RON?
- 'CAUSE I ALREADY SPENT IT.
- REALLY?
HOW DID--NEVER MIND.
UH, I THINK I'LL JUST TAKE
ANOTHER FULL POLISH.
CAN I CUT IN LINE AGAIN?
- I FEEL RIGHT AT HOME
AS A SHOESHINE.
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT I'M DOING,
BUT I KNOW I'M DOING IT
REALLY, REALLY WELL.
- OKAY, LET'S GET GOIN'
WITH THE SPIRIT OF PAWNEE.
ANN, YOU GO FIRST.
- OKAY.
UM...OKAY.
WELL, SINCE IT'S
THE PARKS DEPARTMENT,
I THOUGHT I WOULD DESIGN
A PRETTY PARK.
WITH, UH, DOGS PLAYING.
I CAN'T REALLY DRAW,
SO I JUST CUT SOME STUFF
OUT OF A MAGAZINE.
- THAT LOOKS LIKE SOMETHING
A DEATH ROW CONVICT
WOULD MAKE IN ART THERAPY.
- DUDE, I TRIED.
- AND YOU FAILED.
- IT'S DOGS AND PEOPLE
PLAYING IN A PARK.
- IT'S CUTE!
- IT'S OKAY, SWEETHEART.
YOU CAN'T MAKE ART
BECAUSE YOU ARE ART.
YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL...
BUT THAT SUCKS.
- OKAY. LET'S SEE YOURS!
- FINE. MINE IS AMAZING.
IT'S GONNA BLOW YOUR MIND.
OKAY. SOME PROFESSIONAL-ASS
ART RIGHT HERE.
- I'M NOT QUITE SURE
WHAT I'M LOOKING AT.
- IT'S ABSTRACT, LESLIE.
OVER HERE,
YOU GOT SOME SHAPES.
AND THEN YOU COME
OVER TO THIS SIDE...
YOU KNOW, IT'S ACTUALLY
KIND OF INTERESTING.
EACH SHAPE
IS ITS OWN THING...
BUT THEN WHEN IT COMES
TOGETHER,
IT REALLY GIVES YOU
A SENSE OF...
COMPLETION.
HMM.
A PIECE OF ART CAUSED ME
TO HAVE AN EMOTIONAL REACTION.
IS THAT NORMAL?
- SO IT'S THE LAST SUPPER
BUT WITH FAMOUS PEOPLE
FROM INDIANA.
JOHN MELLANCAMP,
LARRY BIRD,
MICHAEL JACKSON,
DAVID LETTERMAN,
VIVICA A. FOX.
OKAY, SO HERE'S WHERE
IT GETS A LITTLE DICEY,
'CAUSE THERE'S NOT THAT MANY
CELEBRITIES FROM INDIANA,
SO, UM, A NASCAR,
MY FRIEND BECKY,
RON SWANSON, UH...
- DONNA?
WHO'S THE JESUS?
- THAT WOULD BE GREG KINNEAR.
- I DIDN'T KNOW
HE WAS FROM INDIANA.
- YEAH, YOU KNOW,
I READ THAT HE WAS.
- DO YOU THINK
HE'S THE BEST CHOICE FOR JESUS?
I MEAN,
HE WAS GREAT ON ER...
- GREG KINNEAR WASN'T IN ER.
- YEAH, HE WAS.
- I DON'T THINK THAT HE WAS.
- WHO AM I THINKING OF?
OKAY. NEXT.
- [exhales]
[clears throat]
- WOW. REALLY GOOD, JERRY.
- FOR MY MURINAL,
I WAS INSPIRED
BY THE DEATH OF MY GRANDMA--
- [laughing]
YOU SAID "MURINAL."
[laughter]
- NO, I DIDN'T.
- YES, YOU DID.
YOU SAID "MURINAL."
I HEARD IT.
- ANYWAY, SHE--
- JERRY...
WHY DON'T YOU PUT THAT MURINAL
IN THE MEN'S ROOM
SO PEOPLE CAN MURINATE
ALL OVER IT?
[laughter]
- JERRY.
GO TO THE DOCTOR.
YOU MIGHT HAVE
A MURINARY TRACT INFECTION.
- JUST WANTED TO SHOW YOU
MY ART.
all, chanting:
MURINAL, MURINAL, MURINAL!
- DISQUALIFIED!
[laughter]
- IT'S POINTILLISM.
AND EACH DOT IS A PHOTO
OF A CITIZEN OF THE TOWN.
- NO ONE CARES.
AT ALL.
[laughing]
- OKAY, SO THIS IS
A MULTIMEDIA PROJECT.
FIRST...A BUNCH OF RATS
MADE OUT OF GARBAGE.
AND, UM...
THIS IS A TV SCREEN.
IT'LL BE LIKE
A BIG FLAT SCREEN TV,
AND IT'LL PLAY LOOPED VIDEO
OF KNEE SURGERIES.
AND THEN THIS IS
A HUMAN-SIZED HAMSTER WHEEL
THAT WILL BE NEXT
TO THE MURAL,
IF WE CAN GET ONE,
AND IT'LL BE SPINNING,
AND THERE'LL BE LIKE
A FAT GUY IN IT ALL THE TIME
LIKE SCREAMING
AND LIKE EATING RAW BEEF
AND LIKE BLEEDING,
AND LIKE BLOOD WILL COME
OUT OF HIS MOUTH AND STUFF.
AND THAT'LL BE LIKE
RIGHT NEXT TO...THE MURAL.
- I HAVE ONE QUESTION.
WHY?
- IF YOU HAVE TO ASK,
YOU DON'T GET IT.
- I DON'T THINK THEY
REALLY GOT THE ASSIGNMENT.
IF WE'RE GONNA BEAT
ALL THE OTHER DEPARTMENTS,
WE HAVE TO CHOOSE SOMETHING THAT
WILL STAND THE TEST OF TIME...
LIKE THE MONA LISA
OR THE MUSIC OF SQUEEZE.
JUNE 8, 1922.
THE PAWNEE BREAD FACTORY
BURNED TO THE GROUND.
WE LOST A LOT OF GOOD BREAD
THAT DAY...
AS WELL AS
SEVERAL HUMAN LIVES.
AND IT ALSO MADE THE WHOLE
TOWN SMELL LIKE TOAST,
WHICH ONE RESIDENT DESCRIBED
AS "DISTURBINGLY ENTICING."
BUT I DIGRESS.
THE POINT IS,
WE REBUILT PAWNEE
TO THE WONDERFUL TOWN
THAT IT IS TODAY.
- WHY WOULD YOU WANT A MURAL
THAT SHOWS PEOPLE DYING
WHEN YOU COULD HAVE SHAPES
THAT COME ALIVE?
- WELL, BECAUSE
IT'S THE MOST FAMOUS EVENT
IN OUR TOWN'S HISTORY,
AND PEOPLE
LOVE VOTING FOR TRAGEDY.
LOOK AT THE OSCARS.
THIS IS OUR HOLOCAUST MOVIE.
THIS IS OUR ENGLISH PATIENT.
- SOUNDS LIKE YOU'RE
EXPLOITING THE TRAGEDY.
- SEE? ANN GETS IT.
OKAY...TIME TO VOTE, EVERYBODY.
CAST YOUR VOTES!
MAY THE BEST,
MOST TRAGIC PROJECT WIN.
WHEN WE STARTED THIS,
WE WERE SIX DIFFERENT VOICES
WITH SIX IDEAS FOR A MURAL.
AND THEN THOSE SIX VOICES
CAME TOGETHER AS A TEAM.
THERE ARE NO LOSERS TODAY.
BUT THERE IS
ONE WINNER. US.
THE PARKS DEPARTMENT.
TOM, THE RESULTS
OF THE VOTE, PLEASE.
- ONE TO ONE TO ONE
TO ONE TO ONE TO ONE.
- WE ALL VOTED
FOR OURSELVES, DIDN'T WE?
- YEAH. OKAY.
- [softly]
THIRD TIME TODAY.
- MM. THAT'S
A GOOD SHOESHINE.
MM-MM!
[groans] OHH...
MM!
- AH HA HA HA!
EHH!
WHAT THE [bleep], MAN?
- I D-I DON'T KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED.
FRANKLY.
- I EMITTED A NOISE.
THE NOISE WAS INVOLUNTARY.
SOMETIMES A SOUND
IS JUST A SOUND, YOU KNOW?
- WE NEED TO WHITTLE
THESE DOWN.
CAN WE ALL AGREE ON ELIMINATING
ANY OF THESE DESIGNS?
- ANN'S BLOWS.
- WOW. DON'T HOLD BACK.
- NO OFFENSE, BUT IT'S
A GIANT PICTURE OF A PARK.
THAT'S NOT ART.
- WELL, AT LEAST IT'S NOT
A FAT HUMAN HAMSTER EATING MEAT.
- YOU DON'T EVEN WORK HERE!
- OKAY, GUYS.
YOU BOTH HAVE A POINT.
ANN, YOURS WAS A LITTLE TRITE.
AND, APRIL, YOURS WAS HELLISH
AND MIGHT MAKE SOMEONE VOMIT.
- THANK YOU.
- LOOK, THERE'S SOMETHING
ABOUT THOSE SHAPES.
THERE'S SOME EMOTIONAL ART
RIGHT THERE.
- ANY KID COULD DO THAT.
- NO KID COULD DO THAT!
ONLY GOD COULD DO THAT!
- WHAT IS SO GREAT
ABOUT THE SHAPES?
- HE LIKES THE SHAPES, OKAY?
AND HE'S PART OF THE TEAM.
SO HERE, TAKE THESE SCISSORS
AND CUT OUT
YOUR FAVORITE SHAPES.
AND THEN WE'LL PUT THEM
ON A NEW TEAM MURAL.
WE'RE GONNA MAKE A NEW DESIGN
THAT TAKES THE BEST PARTS
OF ALL OF OUR DESIGNS.
IT'S LIKE IF YOU GOT
MICHELANGELO AND ANDY WARHOL
AND JACKSON POLLOCK
AND JIM DAVIS FROM GARFIELD
TO DO ONE PAINTING.
IMAGINE HOW GOOD
THAT PAINTING WOULD BE!
I THINK IT'S REALLY GOOD.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
BRENDANAWICZ,
WE NEED YOU FOR SOMETHING.
- CAN IT WAIT?
I AM SO SWAMPED HERE.
- ANN'S IN TROUBLE.
WE THINK IT MIGHT BE PILLS.
- WHAT?
- NO. THAT'S A LIE.
BUT THIS IS JUST AS IMPORTANT.
WE NEED YOU TO LOOK AT
A PIECE OF ART.
- OH, GOD.
WHAT IS THAT?
- THIS IS OUR ENTRY
FOR THE MURAL CONTEST.
WE COULDN'T DECIDE
ON ONE DESIGN,
SO WE TOOK PARTS
THAT WE ALL LIKED OF OUR DESIGNS
AND THEN WE JUST KIND OF...
SMOOSHED IT INTO A THING.
- WELL, YOU MADE A CAMEL.
YOU'VE NEVER HEARD THAT SAYING?
A CAMEL IS ACTUALLY A HORSE
DESIGNED BY A COMMITTEE,
AND WHAT YOU GUYS HAVE HERE
IS ONE UGLY CAMEL...
FEATURING BILL PAXTON.
- GREG KINNEAR.
- RIGHT. GREG KINNEAR.
- OH! IS BILL PAXTON
FROM INDIANA?
- YOU HAVE TO SAVE US.
YOU HAVE TO DESIGN SOMETHING.
- LESLIE, I'M NOT AN ARTIST.
- YES, YOU ARE.
I'VE SEEN YOU SKETCH THINGS.
- UH, YEAH.
LIKE POLES FOR STOP SIGNS.
- THAT EVERYBODY STOPS
AND LOOKS AT.
- BY LAW, LESLIE.
THEY'RE REQUIRED TO.
- LOOK, MARK, PLEASE.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE OF US
WHO'S ACTUALLY GOT ANY TALENT.
I KNOW
YOU'LL DO SOMETHING GOOD.
AND I REALLY,
REALLY WANT TO WIN THIS.
PLEASE?
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO TONIGHT?
- I WAS GONNA GO TO ARBY'S
AND WATCH FRONTLINE.
- OKAY, HERE WE GO.
- OKAY, SO...IT IS AN OLD MAN
FEEDING PIGEONS IN A PARK.
UH...THE SPIRIT OF PAWNEE,
MAYBE?
- YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
- HOW IS THAT BETTER
THAN MY PARK SCENE?
- IT ISN'T.
AND THAT'S SAYING SOMETHING.
- AND WHO'S THE MAN?
IS HE FAMOUS?
IS IT MARTIN LANDAU?
- LOOK, I HAVE NO DOG
IN THIS FIGHT.
I'M JUST SAYING
THAT THIS'LL WIN.
- IT'S NOTHING.
IT'S MUSH!
THERE'S NOT EVEN ONE SHAPE
IN THERE, MARK!
WHERE ARE THE SHAPES?
- I'M NOT SAYING
THIS IS ANY GOOD.
I'M SAYING THAT THIS'LL WIN.
IT'S MASS APPEAL.
IT'S LIKE WHAT MOTELS PUT UP,
AND IT HANGS THERE FOR YEARS,
AND NO ONE EVER THROWS ACID
AT IT.
- MM. WHO DID THIS?
I LIKE IT.
- SERIOUSLY?
I MEAN--
[whispers]
SORRY!
- YEAH. IT COMFORTS ME.
THAT'LL WIN.
- THIS IS...
GARBAGE!
WE'VE GOTTA GO BACK
TO THE SHAPES.
- NO, THIS IS BORING--WE'VE
GOT TO GO BACK TO THE GARBAGE.
- I WOULD TAKE THE SHAPES
OVER THIS--I MEAN, COME ON!
- I WOULDN'T TAKE THE SHAPES
OVER ANYTHING.
I'D TAKE JERRY'S MURINAL
OVER THIS.
- NO, GUYS...
THIS IS THE ONE.
- WHAT?
- SORRY. MARK'S RIGHT.
- THIS IS AN OUTRAGE!
MARK'S NOT EVEN
IN THE DEPARTMENT.
- NEITHER IS ANN.
- BUT ANN'S HOT.
AND THAT COUNTS FOR SOMETHING.
- WHATEVER HAPPENED TO,
"WE'RE THE PARKS DEPARTMENT.
"RAH, RAH, RAH.
DOWN WITH
THE SEWAGE DEPARTMENT"?
- YEAH, WE SPENT ALL DAY HERE
FOR NO REASON!
- WE HAVE A REASON!
WE'RE GONNA WIN.
THAT'S OUR REASON!
OUR DESIGNS ARE NOT GONNA WIN.
MARK'S MIGHT WIN!
HOW GREAT WOULD IT BE
IF WE WON, YOU GUYS?
YOU'LL FEEL A LOT BETTER,
I PROMISE YOU,
AFTER YOU WIN.
WE'RE GOIN' WITH THIS ONE.
- [groaning]
- I'LL SEE YOU
AT THE PRESENTATION TOMORROW.
THAT IS AN ORDER, TEAM.
GO, TEAM!
TEAM DISMISSED.
YES, WE ARE A TEAM,
BUT I AM THE TEAM LEADER.
SO I MADE A BOLD DECISION.
WE'RE PLAYING IT SAFE.
- HEY, KNOPE.
HOW'S LIFE
IN THE PARKS DE-FART-MENT?
- BETTER THAN LIFE
IN THE SEWAGE DE-FART-MENT.
WHICH MAKES MORE SENSE.
- WHATEVER!
YOU GUYS ARE SCREWED.
GET USED TO THIS.
BECAUSE IT'S GONNA BE
HANGIN' ON THE WALL
RIGHT OUTSIDE YOUR DOOR
FOR THE NEXT 100 YEARS!
- THAT WAS PRETTY GOOD.
YOU THINK THEY'RE GONNA WIN?
- NO.
NO. THEY WENT SUPER-PATRIOTIC.
IT'S A CLASSIC MISTAKE.
IT SEEMS CROWD-PLEASING,
BUT IT'S STILL A STANCE.
AND IN GOVERNMENT,
THERE'S ALWAYS SOMEONE
WHO'LL OPPOSE A STANCE.
US...OLD MAN FEEDING PIGEONS--
NO STANCE.
ABSOLUTELY NO POINT OF VIEW
WHATSOEVER.
- NO POINT OF VIEW.
SMART.
- NO. I HAVEN'T BEEN BACK.
I WISH HIM GOOD LUCK
IN HIS BUSINESS,
AND, YES, I WILL
ABSOLUTELY GO BACK
TO GET MY SHOES SHINED SOON.
I DON'T FRANKLY SEE
WHY THIS IS A TOPIC
FOR DISCUSSION.
- HEY.
OH, HEY, RON.
WHAT'S UP?
- UH...
ANDY...
YOU KNOW THE, UH,
THE THING?
THE OTHER DAY?
- OTHER DAY...OTHER DAY...
OH, UH...YESTERDAY?
- I AM...
THAT WAS--THAT WAS--
- YOU KNOW,
I'D BE OKAY IF WE...
[clears throat]
[whispers] I'D BE OKAY IF WE
NEVER MENTIONED IT AGAIN.
- NEVER MENTIONED WHAT AGAIN?
- THE MOAN, RON.
THE WEIRD MOAN YOU MADE
THAT WAS SUPER-WEIRD?
DO YOU NOT REMEMBER THAT?
I TALKED ABOUT IT WITH THE LADY
WHO WENT AFTER YOU FOR 1/2 HOUR.
SHE SAID SHE THOUGHT
IT WAS AN ANIMAL--
- OKAY.
IT WAS JUST AN ODD MOMENT.
LET'S JUST NOT
TALK ABOUT IT ANYMORE.
- THAT'S WHAT
I WAS TRYING TO SAY.
BUT, YEAH...OKAY.
- OKAY.
- GOOD JOB.
- MISS KNOPE.
- CHIEF KONNER.
WHAT DO YOU GOT THERE?
- WELL, WE AREN'T REALLY
ARTISTS,
BUT WE GAVE IT A SHOT.
IT'S YOUR BASIC
DOGS PLAYING POKER, BUT...
WITH AN-EVERYTHING'S-ON-FIRE
THEME.
THIS IS MY NEPHEW OVER HERE.
- MM.
- AND THIS IS AN ATTRACTIVE LADY
WITH A HAMBURGER FOR A HEAD.
JUST SOME STUFF WE LIKE,
YOU KNOW?
ANYWAY, WE HAD A LOT OF FUN
PUTTING IT TOGETHER.
[laughs]
- WELL, GOOD LUCK!
- THANKS.
WE THINK IT'S A WINNER.
- GO AHEAD.
- WHAT?
- THE CAMEL'S WAY MORE FUN.
- I WANT MY TEAM BACK.
AND MY TEAM MADE THIS
HOT, CRAZY CAMEL MESS.
SO THIS IS WHAT
WE'RE GONNA SUBMIT,
EVEN IF IT MEANS WE LOSE.
GOD, I HOPE WE WIN.
BUT WE'RE DEFINITELY GONNA LOSE.
- PROBABLY.
- ALL RIGHT!
LET'S GET IN THERE AND SHOW 'EM
HOW PARKS GETS IT DONE!
- AND ANN!
HOW ANN GETS IT DONE!
- YES.
- LET'S GO!
[pen clicking]
[click click click click]
- WHAT ARE THE SHAPES?
- THE SHAPES ARE AWESOME,
IS WHAT THEY ARE.
YOU CAN'T HANDLE IT.
- NO, I-I ACTUALLY LIKE THEM.
- FORGIVE ME.
IS THAT MICHAEL JACKSON?
- HEE HEE--YES.
THE PRIDE OF INDIANA.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
SO IT'S RELEVANT.
- WHO IS HE CARRYING?
- JESUS GREG KINNEAR.
- YOU KNOW, IT LOOKS LIKE
HE'S CARRYING KINNEAR
INTO THE BURNING BUILDING.
- OH, WELL, THAT'S BECAUSE
HE'S MOONWALKING.
SO HE, UM...SHOULD BE
GOIN' THE OTHER WAY.
THAT DID NOT OCCUR TO ME.
- [laughing]
[laughter]
- SORRY.
- SO THERE YOU GO.
THE SPIRIT OF PAWNEE.
WE DIDN'T WIN.
BUT NEITHER DID ANYONE ELSE.
THEY REALIZED IT WAS GONNA
COST A TON OF MONEY
TO HIRE A MURALIST.
SO THEY'RE JUST GONNA
RESTORE THE OLD ONE.
THEY'RE CHANGING THE TITLE
TO THE DIVERSITY EXPRESS.
OH, WELL.
- [laughs] AW!
- YAY.
- YAY!
- AH! LOOK AT THAT.
- NO, NO! IT'S NOT
AS GOOD AS THE OTHER ONE.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU MEAN BY GOOD.
- NEITHER DO I!
JUST DO ANOTHER ONE!
- YOU KNOW,
I HAVE ACTUAL ASSIGNMENTS
THAT I HAVE TO FINISH
FOR ART SCHOOL.
- SHUT UP AND DO
MORE ART FOR ME.
- [sighs]
- THIS ONE'S RACIST.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
I'VE LOOKED AT THIS
FOR FIVE HOURS NOW.
I LIKE THE GREEN ONE
AND THE RED CIRCLE RIGHT HERE.
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
- [voice breaking]
I'M TEARING UP, MAN.