- THANK YOU, OLD GUS,
FOR BRIGHTENING OUR LIVES,
OUR HEARTS
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY
OUR SHOES.
[applause]
- THIS TRULY IS A DAY
OF MIXED EMOTIONS FOR ME.
I'M SAD THAT OLD GUS
IS LEAVING.
BUT IT ALLOWS ME TO HELP ANDY
RESTART HIS LIFE
AS PIONEER HALL'S
NEW SHOESHINE GUY.
- WELL, I'VE BEEN LISTENING
TO YOUR BORING SPEECHES
FOR THE LAST 50 YEARS.
AND NOW IT'S TIME FOR YOU
TO LISTEN TO ONE OF MINE.
YOU KNOW A DAY LIKE THIS
MAKES A MAN REFLECT
UPON HIS LIFE.
AND I'VE COME
TO THE CONCLUSION
THAT I'VE COMPLETELY
WASTED MINE.
AND JUST FOR THE RECORD,
I NEVER EVER LIKED BEING CALLED
OLD GUS.
I DIDN'T UNDERSTAND IT
WHEN I WAS IN MY 20S
AND I SURE HATE IT NOW.
SO GO TO HELL,
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF YOU.
SCREW PAWNEE AND SCREW
YOUR DAMN SHOES.
AH!
- OLD GUS IS CLASSIC.
[upbeat music]
*
- SO I PROPOSE THAT WE
CHANGE OUR NAME
FROM THE SUBCOMMITTEE
FOR PIT BEAUTIFICATION
TO THE SUBCOMMITTEE
FOR LOT BEAUTIFICATION.
APRIL, STOP THAT.
WHO ARE YOU TEXTING?
- YOU.
- AWW.
SHE'S TEXTING ME.
I'M SORRY YOU'RE BORED.
- UH, HEY, EVERYONE.
OH, HEY, ANN.
UM, LESLIE, CAN I TALK
TO YOU FOR A MINUTE?
- FINE. TOM YOU'RE IN CHARGE.
KEEP THE MOMENTUM GOING.
KEEP THESE MINDS WORKING.
- ABSOLUTELY, CHIEF.
- OKAY, WOULD YOU RATHER
BE ABLE TO FLY
OR SPEAK FLUENT FRENCH?
DONNA, GO.
- FRENCH.
- I DON'T WANNA FREAK YOU OUT,
BUT ANOTHER DEPARTMENT
FILED A PLANNING CLAIM
FOR LOT 48.
- WHO?
NO...
- YEAH.
- DAMN IT!
THE LIBRARY?
PAWNEE'S LIBRARY DEPARTMENT
IS THE MOST DIABOLICAL,
RUTHLESS BUNCH OF BUREAUCRATS
I'VE EVER SEEN.
THEY'RE LIKE A BIKER GANG.
BUT INSTEAD OF SHOTGUNS
AND CRYSTAL METH
THEY USE POLITICAL SAVVY.
AND SHUSHING.
- IT'S GONNA BE OKAY.
IT'S NOT A DONE DEAL.
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
THANKS FOR PULLING ME
OUT OF THERE.
I NEED A GOOD PLAN, THOUGH.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T
WANT TO CAUSE A PANIC.
NEWS FLASH, WE'RE SCREWED.
WE GOT A BIG PROBLEM
WITH THE LIBRARY.
- PUNK ASS BOOK JOCKEYS.
- WAIT, WHY DO WE HATE
THE LIBRARY?
- THE LIBRARY IS THE WORST
GROUP OF PEOPLE
EVER ASSEMBLED IN HISTORY.
THEY'RE MEAN,
CONNIVING, RUDE
AND EXTREMELY WELL READ,
WHICH MAKES THEM VERY DANGEROUS.
AND THEY'RE TRYING TO STEAL
LOT 48 FOR A NEW BRANCH.
all: WHAT?
- YEAH.
- GET OUT OF HERE.
- ON 48?
- YEAH!
- THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
- I ACTUALLY THINK A LIBRARY
WOULD BE NICE
THAT CLOSE TO MY HOUSE.
BUT I'M NOT ABOUT TO SAY THAT
IN THERE.
- A NEW BRANCH?
- YES!
- OH, I HATE THEM.
- OKAY, WE NEED TO MAKE CONTACT
WITH SOMEONE THERE.
DOES ANYBODY KNOW ANYBODY
THAT WORKS AT THE LIBRARY?
- UH, WELL, WE ACTUALLY
KIND OF DO.
THE NEW DEPUTY DIRECTOR
OF THE DEPARTMENT
IS TAMMY SWANSON.
- RON'S EX-WIFE?
THAT'S TERRIFIC.
OR IS THAT AWFUL?
I MEAN, HE HATES HER,
BUT HE KNOWS HER.
EVERYTHING'S OKAY.
OR IS IT JUST THE SAME?
- LESLIE, YOU'RE THINKING
OUT LOUD AGAIN.
- AM I?
I AM.
- OF COURSE, THAT BITCH
OF AN EX-WIFE
IS WORKING FOR
THE LIBRARY NOW.
THAT IS PERFECT.
THE WORST PERSON IN THE WORLD
WORKING AT THE WORST PLACE
IN THE WORLD.
- I HAVE TO GO TALK TO HER.
AND YOU GOTTA GIVE ME
SOMETHING I CAN USE.
DOES SHE HAVE ANY WEAKNESSES?
- NO.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN NO?
EVERYBODY HAS A WEAKNESS.
-NOT MACHINES.
I HONESTLY BELIEVE
THAT SHE WAS PROGRAMMED
BY SOMEONE FROM THE FUTURE
TO COME BACK AND DESTROY
ALL HAPPINESS.
- I SEE.
JUST, I KNEW THAT YOU HAD
TWO EX-WIVES NAMED TAMMY.
SO I WAS HOPING THAT
THERE WAS ONE
THAT YOU GOT ALONG WITH.
- NO.
I HATE 'EM BOTH.
ON MY DEATH BED,
MY FINAL WISH IS TO HAVE
MY EX-WIVES RUSHED TO MY SIDE
SO I CAN USE MY DYING BREATH
TO TELL THEM BOTH TO GO TO HELL
ONE LAST TIME.
WOULD I GET MARRIED AGAIN?
OH, ABSOLUTELY.
IF YOU DON'T BELIEVE IN LOVE,
WHAT'S THE POINT OF LIVING?
- I'M JUST LOOKING FORWARD
TO A THOUGHTFUL DEBATE
WITH TAMMY ABOUT
THE RELATIVE MERITS
OF PARKS VERSUS LIBRARIES.
AND IN CASE SOMETHING BAD
GOES DOWN,
I WORE MY SHARPEST RINGS.
THIS ONE WILL TEAR YOU UP.
HELLO.
HI.
I'M LESLIE KNOPE.
I CALLED A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
- YOU HAVE A LOT OF NERVE
SHOWING YOUR FACE HERE.
- EXCUSE ME?
- YOU HAVE OVERDUE BOOK FEES
TOTALING $3.00 MISSY.
- THAT IS SO TYPICAL.
I SHOULD'VE KNOWN YOU'D USE
A LOW-BLOW,
DIRTY POOL, B.S. MOVE
LIKE THAT.
THAT'S WHY EVERYBODY HATES
THE LIBRARY.
HERE, YOU KNOW WHAT,
HERE'S YOUR $3.00.
AND I'LL SEE YOU IN HELL.
- LESLIE, LESLIE, LESLIE,
I WAS JUST KIDDING.
MY GOSH.
I MEAN, YOU DID HAVE $3.00
WORTH OF FINES,
BUT I CLEARED THEM.
WE GOVERNMENT GALS
HAVE TO WATCH
EACH OTHER'S BACKS, RIGHT?
- I KNOW THIS IS A TRAP.
BUT I DON'T KNOW HOW.
- OKAY.
DID YOU TALK TO RON?
UM, RON TENDS TO EXAGGERATE
WHEN IT COMES TO ME.
I SWEAR I DON'T HAVE
CLOVEN FEET.
PLEASE, SIT DOWN.
-SHINE, SHINE,
SHINE YOUR SHOES?
WHAT DO YOU SAY, SIR?
MA'AM, SHOESHINE?
I WON'T LOOK UP YOUR SKIRT.
- ANN, WHOA.
OH, MY GOSH--CRAZY!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
IT'S ME, IT'S ANDY.
- HI, ANDY.
- SO, ANN, HOW YOU BEEN?
- GOOD.
YEAH, LESLIE TOLD ME
YOU WERE WORKING HERE NOW.
- YEAH, JUST JOINING
THE RAT RACE.
CHASING THE CHEESE.
RACING THE RATS.
TRYING TO GET THE CHEESE.
ENOUGH TECHNICAL BUSINESS TALK.
YOU LOOK RAVISHING.
- NOT A LOT OF CUSTOMERS,
HUH?
- YEAH, BUSINESS
IS A LITTLE SLOW.
IT IS DEFINITELY DUE TO
THE ECONOMY.
UM, I'VE BEEN HEARING A LOT
OF PEOPLE SAY THAT A LOT
ABOUT A LOT OF STUFF.
WHOA, MARK!
YOU WANT THOSE SHOES SHINED?
I'LL GIVE YOU A DISCOUNT BECAUSE
YOU'RE A FRIEND OF ANN'S.
- WELL, I'M MORE THAN
A FRIEND OF ANN'S.
- OH, NOT FOR LONG.
- I'M SORRY?
- I DON'T KNOW.
AT LEAST HE FINALLY HAS
A REAL JOB.
WHEN WE WERE DATING
THE ONLY JOB HE HAD
WAS SENDING AUDITION TAPES
TO SURVIVOR
AND DEAL OR NO DEAL.
- HI, MY NAME IS ANDY DWYER,
AND I WOULD BE A PERFECT
CONTESTANT FOR DEAL OR NO DEAL.
- I WANT IT TO BE
A PERFECT PARK,
WITH A STATE-OF-THE-ART
SWING SET
AND BASKETBALL COURTS.
AND OFF TO THE SIDE
A LOVELY SITTING AREA
FOR KIDS WITH ASTHMA TO WATCH
OTHER KIDS PLAY.
WOW, IF I'D HAD A PARK
LIKE THAT
WHEN I WAS GROWING UP
I PROBABLY WOULDN'T
HAVE GONE THROUGH
SUCH A PROLONGED
MALL SLUT PHASE.
- WELL, THAT'S--THAT'S
THE GOAL, TAMMY.
- LISTEN, YOU GUYS
GOT THERE FIRST.
I'M GONNA WITHDRAW MY REQUEST
FOR THE LOT
AS A PROFESSIONAL COURTESY
TO YOU.
GOVERNMENT GALS, RIGHT?
- GOVERNMENT GALS.
- SO YOU TALKED TO TAMMY.
WHAT'S IT LIKE TO STARE
INTO THE EYE
OF SATAN'S BUTT HOLE?
- SHE'S CHANGED, RON.
SHE'S A DIFFERENT PERSON.
I JUST--I THINK
IT WOULD BE HEALTHY
FOR YOU TO GET A SENSE
OF CLOSURE.
LOOK AT MARK AND ME.
WE SLEPT TOGETHER.
WE TALKED ABOUT IT.
WE'RE STILL FRIENDS.
- YOU SLEPT WITH BRENDANAWICZ?
- NO!
- LOOK, TAMMY AND I
DON'T WORK.
WE ARE OIL AND WATER.
OR OIL AND TNT AND C-4
AND A DETONATOR
AND A BUTANE TORCH.
NOTHING GOOD WILL COME...
WAIT...
SHE'S HERE, ISN'T SHE?
- HI, RON.
- TAMMY.
- GOOD.
GOOD START.
- I'M SORRY ABOUT THIS,
BUT I JUST REALLY
WANT TO TALK TO YOU.
COULDN'T WE GO HAVE
A CUP OF COFFEE?
- LET'S GET THIS OVER WITH.
- THANKS, RON.
IT MEANS A LOT.
YOU'RE A MIRACLE WORKER.
- DO YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU JUST DID?
- YES, DONNA.
I GOT TWO PEOPLE TO PUT ASIDE
YEARS OF HOSTILITY
AND OPEN A DOOR TO
THE POSSIBILITY OF FRIENDSHIP.
- YOU WERE NOT HERE WHEN
RON AND TAMMY GOT DIVORCED.
I WAS.
THOSE TWO ARE CRAZY.
- YEAH, AND YOU
JUST OPENED THE GATES.
TO CRAZY TOWN.
- FRANKLY, I THINK RON
WAS ACTING LIKE A BABY.
A LITTLE BIT.
I MEAN, WHAT IS HE AFRAID OF?
TAMMY'S JUST A WOMAN.
A NICE WOMAN.
YOU KNOW,
SHE'S NOT A MURDERER.
SHE'S NOT A DRAGON.
- IT'S REALLY GOOD
TO SEE YOU, RON.
- YOU'VE AGED HORRIBLY.
- YOU SON OF A BITCH.
- THAT DIDN'T TAKE LONG.
- OH, MY GOD!
WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM?
NOTHING'S CHANGED, HAS IT?
WHO SET THE BED ON FIRE?
- EXCUSE ME, FOLKS.
- I DID, OKAY.
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANNA HEAR?
[overlapping chatter]
- PLEASE.
PLEASE.
- WHEN YOU MEDDLE IN
SOMEONE'S PERSONAL LIFE
IT'S JUST SO REWARDING.
- OH, GOD!
YEAH!
OH GOD, YEAH!
OH, GOD!
OH, YES, BABY!
GUN IT!
USUAL PLACE?
[laughing]
- * HAVE GUN WILL TRAVEL
* READS THE CARD OF A MAN
* A KNIGHT WITHOUT ARMOR
IN A SAVAGE LAND *
GOOD MORNING, JERRY.
THAT IS A BEAUTIFUL
SWEATER VEST.
APRIL!
YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU COULD USE $20.00.
AM I RIGHT?
- WHY?
- 'CAUSE YOU'RE A KID
AND KIDS ALWAYS NEED MONEY.
- I NEED MONEY.
- HA!
THAT'S WHY
YOU'RE MY FAVORITE, TOM.
- WHEN TIGER WOODS
FEELS INVINCIBLE
HE WEARS A RED SHIRT
AND BLACK PANTS.
- GOOD MORNING, DEPUTY.
- RON WEARS THE SAME THING
AFTER HE'S HAD SEX.
- I'M A SIMPLE MAN.
I LIKE PRETTY,
DARK-HAIRED WOMEN
AND BREAKFAST FOOD.
BUT THIS STOCK PHOTO
I BOUGHT AT A FRAMING STORE
ISN'T REAL.
TODAY I GOT THE REAL THING.
A NAKED TAMMY MADE ME
BREAKFAST THIS MORNING.
I SHOULD'VE TAKEN
A PICTURE OF IT.
- HEY, TOM.
- WHAT'S UP?
- MY GIRLFRIEND'S EX IS WORKING
100 FEET AWAY FROM MY DESK.
AND HE'S BEEN PRETTY CLEAR
ABOUT WANTING HER BACK.
WHAT DO I DO WITH THAT?
- HMM.
THAT'S A TOUGH ONE.
- YOU SHOULD BREAK UP WITH HER
AND TELL HER TO GO OUT WITH ME.
- THAT'S GOOD.
CAN I ASK YOU ANOTHER QUESTION?
WHY DID I COME TO YOU
FOR ADVICE?
- YEAH, OKAY.
I THINK YOU SHOULD
PLAY THIS ONE COOL, MAN.
BE THE GROWN-UP.
TAKE THE HIGH ROAD.
- YEAH.
- ANN'S A CLASSY CHICK.
IF YOU GET DOWN IN THE MUD,
YOU'RE JUST GONNA LOSE
HER RESPECT.
- UH...
YOU'VE JUST MADE A SURPRISING
AMOUNT OF SENSE, TOM.
THANK YOU.
- I'VE NEVER TAKEN
THE HIGH ROAD.
BUT I TELL OTHER PEOPLE TO.
'CAUSE THEN THERE'S MORE ROOM
FOR ME ON THE LOW ROAD.
- SO HOW DID YOUR COFFEE
WITH TAMMY GO?
- LESLIE, I CAN'T
THANK YOU ENOUGH
FOR STICKING YOUR NOSE
WHERE IT DIDN'T BELONG.
- I KNEW IT.
SO WHAT DID YOU GUYS
TALK ABOUT?
OLD TIMES?
I LOVE TALKING ABOUT OLD TIMES.
NEW TIMES ARE GREAT TOO.
BUT THERE'S JUST SOMETHING
ABOUT OLD TIMES.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- WE DIDN'T TALK.
WE MADE LOVE.
- OH, MY, MMM...
GOOD.
OH, WELL, SPARE ME THE DETAILS.
I'M JUST HAPPY--
- IT WAS SO INTENSE.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHERE MY FLESH
STOPPED AND HERS BEGAN.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- YEAH.
- OUR MARRIAGE WAS ALWAYS
A COMPLETE DISASTER,
BUT WE DID HAVE THAT,
THE TWO OF US.
IT'S LIKE DOING PEYOTE
AND SNEEZING SLOWLY
FOR SIX HOURS.
- THIS SEEMS
LIKE A PRIVATE MATTER.
BUT I'M JUST SO--
- THAT WOMAN REALLY KNOWS
HER WAY AROUND A PENIS.
- [sighing] OKAY.
WELL, I'M HAPPY
THAT IT WENT WELL
AND THAT YOU ENJOYED
YOUR COFFEE.
I TRULY BELIEVE THAT EVERYONE
SHOULD BE FRIENDS
WITH THEIR EXES.
I CAN'T EVEN TELL YOU HOW MANY
OF MY EXES' WEDDINGS
I'VE BEEN TO.
[cackling]
- THEY'RE READING
THEIR OLD DIVORCE PAPERS.
- THREE FISTFULS OF HAIR?
THAT'S NOT EVEN POSSIBLE.
- WELL, I'M TOO CLASSY
TO SAY I TOLD YOU SO, DONNA.
SO I WROTE IT
ON A POST IT.
- LESLIE.
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE
THE REST OF THE DAY OFF.
I MEAN YOU SPEND SO MUCH TIME
WORRYING ABOUT THIS PARK.
BUT REALLY, WHO CARES?
- I CARE.
I CARE A LOT.
IT'S KINDA MY THING.
REMEMBER?
- BUT AT THE END OF THE DAY
WHAT DOES IT MATTER
IF THE LOT BECOMES A PARK
OR A MUSEUM
OR A MEGA CHURCH?
OR A LIBRARY.
- NOBODY SAID LIBRARY.
- RON, YOU'VE BEEN TALKING
TO TAMMY ABOUT THE LOT?
- NO.
I SWEAR ON A GRAVE.
- OH, MY GOD!
RON!
TELL ME THE TRUTH.
ARE YOU GIVING HER THE LOT?
- NOT GIVING.
WE HAVE DISCUSSED A TRADE.
- FOR WHAT?
- [muttering]
- EXCUSE ME.
- MORE SEX.
- OH, GOD!
TAMMY, CAN I SPEAK WITH YOU
FOR A SECOND?
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
YOU DON'T CARE ABOUT RON.
YOU'RE JUST USING HIM TO GET
LOT 48 FOR YOUR LIBRARY.
- LESLIE, THAT'S CRAZY.
AND CORRECT.
- WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
- LES, THERE ARE TWO KINDS
OF WOMEN IN THIS WORLD.
THERE ARE WOMEN
WHO WORK HARD
AND STRESS OUT ABOUT DOING
THE RIGHT THING
AND THEN THERE ARE WOMEN
WHO ARE COOL.
YOU COULD EITHER BE
A CLEOPATRA
OR YOU COULD BE AN
ELEANOR ROOSEVELT.
I'D RATHER BE CLEOPATRA.
- WHAT KIND OF LUNATIC WOULD
WANNA BE CLEOPATRA
OVER ELEANOR ROOSEVELT?
- HAVEN'T YOU EVER MESSED
WITH A MAN'S HEAD
JUST TO SEE WHAT YOU COULD
GET HIM TO DO FOR YOU?
WE DO IT ALL THE TIME
IN THE LIBRARY DEPARTMENT.
YOU SHOULD COME
JOIN US SOMETIME.
- I WOULD NEVER WORK
AT THE LIBRARY DEPARTMENT.
I'M GONNA TELL RON
WHAT YOU JUST SAID.
AND THIS LITTLE GAME THAT
YOU'RE PLAYING
IS GONNA BE OVER.
- OKIE DOKE.
- YEAH, YOU BETTER RUN.
WE'RE NO LONGER
GOVERNMENT GALS.
LOOK, WE NEED TO TALK.
RON, NO.
THE PLANNING DEPARTMENT
REPRIORITIZATION DOCUMENT?
- CALM DOWN.
I HAVEN'T SIGNED IT YET.
- YEAH, WELL, YOU'RE GOING TO.
BECAUSE TAMMY WANTS YOU TO
AND YOU DO EVERYTHING
THAT SHE WANTS.
- SHE MADE SOME REALLY GOOD
POINTS ABOUT LIBRARIES.
- ARE YOU EVEN LISTENING
TO YOURSELF?
YOU'RE DEFENDING
THE LIBRARY NOW?
RON, THE LIBRARY.
OF ALL THE HORRIFYING,
MISERABLE THINGS IN THE WORLD.
- SOME PEOPLE LIKE LIBRARIES.
- I CAN'T EVEN BELIEVE
WHAT I'M HEARING.
SOME PEOPLE LIKE LIBRARIES.
RON, SHE'S IN YOUR HEAD.
YOU SAID THAT SHE WAS
A MANIPULATIVE MONSTER
AND YOU WERE RIGHT.
- NO, NO.
TAMMY'S CHANGED.
- LOOK ME IN THE EYE
AND TELL ME THAT SHE'S CHANGED.
LOOK ME IN THE EYE.
- I'M SO SCREWED NOW.
HER HOOKS ARE IN MY BRAIN.
- YEP.
SHE HAS ALL THE POWER
AND I HAVE NOTHING.
I'M SO LITTLE.
- WHY DON'T YOU JUST BREAK UP
WITH HER?
- I DON'T THINK I CAN.
WE WOULD JUST END UP NAKED.
AND I'D GIVE HER YOUR LOT
AND MY HOUSE
AND GOD KNOWS WHAT ELSE.
I HAVE NO CONTROL
OVER MY ACTIONS.
IT'S LIKE SHE'S CRAWLED UP
INSIDE ME--
- OH, GOD, RON.
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR ABOUT
YOUR DISGUSTING SEX ANYMORE.
OKAY, NOW SACK UP.
YOU ARE RON FREAKIN' SWANSON!
- NOT AROUND HER I'M NOT.
IT TOOK YEARS OF INTENSE,
FOCUSED HATRED
TO GET OVER HER.
AND NOW I'VE UNDONE
ALL THAT GREAT WORK.
YOU'VE GOTTA HELP ME
BREAK UP WITH HER.
- I DON'T THINK I SHOULD
GET INVOLVED IN THIS.
- OH, NOW YOU DON'T WANT TO
GET INVOLVED?
"IT'S JUST COFFEE, RON."
"SHE'S CHANGED, RON."
"I LET MARK NAIL ME
AND WE'RE STILL FRIENDS."
- OKAY, I NEVER--I WOULD NEVER
USE THOSE WORDS.
I NEVER SAID--POINT TAKEN.
LET'S GO DUMP YOUR EX.
- THANK YOU.
- SO WOULD YOU LIKE
TO BE IN THE ROOM
WHEN I TELL HER IT'S OVER
OR WOULD YOU RATHER
WAIT OUTSIDE?
- IN THE ROOM.
I DON'T WANT HER TO THINK
I'M A WIMP.
- HERE ARE THE GROUND RULES.
DON'T TALK TO HER.
DO NOT MAKE EYE CONTACT
WITH HER.
DON'T BELIEVE ANYTHING
SHE SAYS.
JUST SIT THERE
LIKE A POTTED PLANT.
CAN YOU DO THAT?
COME ON.
- DO YOU HAVE ANY TOM--
- MARK!
- HEY.
- HEY! DONNA.
- SO HOW'S
THE SHOESHINE GAME?
- I'M ON A BREAK.
ONE OF THE MANY ADVANTAGES
OF OWNING YOUR OWN BUSINESS.
- YOU KNOW THAT'S NOT
YOUR SITUATION, RIGHT?
- YEAH.
LISTEN, DONNA.
- YES.
- QUICK QUESTION.
ANN IS TRYING TO DECIDE
BETWEEN MARK AND MYSELF.
- NO, SHE'S NOT, ACTUALLY.
- IF YOU HAD TO CHOOSE,
WHO WOULD YOU CHOOSE?
RIGHT NOW, ON THE SPOT.
- I'M NOT SURE.
WHY DON'T YOU SPIN AROUND
FOR ME.
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
CAN WE TALK PRIVATELY?
- SURE.
- JUST OUT HERE.
- MMM, ANDY.
- SO, TAMMY, FOR THAT
AND MANY OTHER REASONS
RON HAS DECIDED TO END
THIS RELATIONSHIP.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
RON BROUGHT YOU HERE
TO BREAK UP WITH ME
FOR HIM?
- SHE VOLUNTEERED.
- LESLIE,
RON DOESN'T WANT TO BREAK UP
WITH ME.
WHAT RON WANTS TO DO
IS LEAVE HERE RIGHT NOW.
GO TO THE SLEAZIEST MOTEL
IN TOWN
AND WRAP HIMSELF AROUND ME
LIKE A COILED SNAKE.
- NO, HE DOESN'T.
- I'M PRETTY SURE HE DOES.
- [groaning]
- SEE? HE'S COMPLETELY
OVER YOU.
- LOOK, I UNDERSTAND THAT
THIS ANN SITUATION
IS AWKWARD.
BUT I LIKE YOU A LOT
AS A DUDE.
AND I JUST HOPE THAT THERE IS
SOME WAY THAT WE CAN BOTH BE
MATURE AND MAYBE BE FRIENDS.
- YEAH, I DOUBT IT.
I MEAN, I THINK
YOU'RE A COOL DUDE TOO.
I LIKE YOU AS WELL.
BUT I'M STILL
IN LOVE WITH ANN.
I COULDN'T HAVE BEEN MORE
UPFRONT ABOUT THAT.
- IS PUNCHING ALLOWED
ON THE HIGH ROAD?
- I'M SORRY, LESLIE.
SHE WINS.
I CAN'T RESIST HER.
- BUT, RON,
YOU HAVE TO.
-STAY OUT OF THIS.
THIS IS OUR RELATIONSHIP.
HE'S MY MAN
AND WE HAVE SOMETHING TWISTED
AND BEAUTIFUL.
OH...
YOU WANT RON.
THAT'S WHAT THIS
IS ALL ABOUT.
- NO, THAT'S INSANE.
FINE, I HAD ONE DREAM,
BUT NO, NO.
- BABY, DON'T YOU SEE
WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE?
SHE'S MANIPULATING YOU
BECAUSE SHE'S JEALOUS OF ME
AND THE THINGS I GET TO DO
TO YOUR BODY AND FACE.
- I'M HERE BECAUSE
RON IS MY FRIEND.
AND I DON'T LIKE SEEING
MY FRIENDS MISERABLE.
AND YOU, TAMMY,
YOU MAKE HIM MISERABLE.
SO, RON, YOU CAN GIVE HER
THE LOT OR DON'T.
WHATEVER.
JUST PLEASE, FIND A WAY
TO BE HAPPY.
- NO, WAIT.
- RON, IT'S OKAY.
JUST SIGN THE THING.
- NO, LESLIE.
IT'S NOT OKAY.
YOU JUST PUT MY NEEDS
IN FRONT OF YOUR OWN.
NO WOMAN HAS EVER DONE THAT
FOR ME BEFORE.
- I'M SURE THAT'S NOT TRUE.
- YOU SEE THE KIND OF WOMEN
THAT I CHOOSE, RIGHT?
LOOK, JUST WAIT FOR ME
DOWNSTAIRS.
IF I'M NOT DOWN
IN FIVE MINUTES,
IT'S ONLY BECAUSE I'M RECEIVING
A PLEASURE SO INTENSE--
- OH, MY GOD!
- WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?
ANDY AND ANN'S
FAMILY SHOESHINE?
- I THOUGHT IT HAD
A NICE RING TO IT.
- OH, MY GOD.
LOOK, MARK HAS BEEN REALLY COOL
ABOUT ALL THIS.
AND YOU'RE THROWING IT
IN HIS FACE.
- BUT I STILL HAVE
FEELINGS FOR YOU.
OKAY.
I SAID IT.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
NOT MENTION THOSE FEELINGS
TO YOUR BOYFRIEND?
- YES!
- YES.
AND YOU MIGHT WANNA TAKE
THESE PICTURES DOWN.
- OH, MY GOD.
TAKE THOSE PICTURES DOWN.
- WHAT?
IT'S FINE.
WHAT DID I--
- ALL OF IT!
- I'M GONNA.
- NOW!
OH, MY GOD.
GIVE ME THE BIKINI ONE.
- THE TEENY ONE?
- BIKINI ONE.
- YOU DIDN'T
GIVE HER THE LOT.
- LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
- IS PART OF YOUR MOUSTACHE
MISSING?
- YES.
JUST KEEP WALKING.
- THERE'S A PUSH PIN
IN YOUR FACE.
- LEAVE IT IN.
CAN'T YOU WALK FASTER?
- MY LEGS ARE SHORTER
THAN YOURS.
- WE HAD A GOOD RUN.
- THANK YOU FOR SAVING
MY FUTURE PARK.
I KNOW THAT MUST HAVE BEEN
HARD FOR YOU.
YOU DIDN'T KILL TAMMY,
DID YOU?
- I'M AFRAID
SHE CAN'T BE KILLED.
TO EXES.
MAY THEY ALWAYS STAY
THAT WAY.
TAMMY IS A MEAN PERSON.
- COME ON, RON.
YOU CAN DO BETTER THAN THAT.
- SHE'S A GRADE-A BITCH.
- THERE WE GO.
- EVERY TIME SHE LAUGHS
AN ANGEL DIES.
EVEN TELEMARKETERS
AVOID HER.
HER BIRTH WAS PAYBACK
FOR THE SINS OF MAN.
BUT YOU KNOW
THE WORST THING ABOUT HER?
- SHE WORKS FOR THE LIBRARY.