CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme music playing)
(bell ringing)
(whistle blowing)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(honking)
D'oh! (screams)
(tires screeching)
Animation is so great.
It's way better than
whatever the alternative is.
Seems like animated shows are everywhere,
or were last year.
Cool. Japanimation.
(grunts and roars)
Electro-web, deploy!
(grunting)
Now I control the roboverse!
(laughing)
Your laugh is incorrect, Meganaut!
Activate prawn power!
(yells)
(grunts, screaming)
Man, that Princess Tempura
is one heck of a transformazoid.
Wait, I'm confused.
Why was a wolf shooting a web?
Cartoons don't have to make sense.
He's right, you know.
Daddy, are you sure it's OK
for us to watch cartoons?
Mm-hmm. This one's fine and dandy, Roddy.
It's approved by a council
of Presbylutheran ministers.
(music playing)
Whatcha making there, Gravey?
It's a pipe bomb, Jobriath,
for to blow up planned parenthood.
I don't know, Gravey.
I'm sick of your lack of faith.
Hmm?
But, Gravey...
-(loud explosion)
-(organ music playing)
BOTH: Yay!
And then, I created the voice
of Yellow-Bellied Yak.
(as cowardly lion)
All I need is some courage.
Courage, I tell you.
Excuse me, but isn't that voice
very similar to the Cowardly Lion?
Also, sir, your Loudmouth Leopard
is a rip-off of Jackie Gleason.
(as Jackie Gleason)
Hamina, hamina, hamina, hamina.
And Klutzy Kat sounds
exactly like Jerry Lewis
with the stealing and the lawsuit!
And, oh, nice judge, don't hurt
a person with the thing.
(music playing)
(moaning)
(kissing sounds)
(screaming)
DIRECTOR: And... cut!
ANNOUNCER: After a tough day on the set,
how do Itchy and Scratchy relax?
With Laramie extra-tar cigarettes.
Here's your smoke, Mr. Itchy.
Thank you, Louie.
(grunts)
Mm-hmm! And now,
there's more nico-glycerol.
I don't know what's in them.
I just know I can't stop smoking them.
(all laughing)
(hacking coughs)
Wait a minute. Was that cat
making out with that mouse?
'Cause if they were...
Folks, you're about to witness
the exciting new process
of motion-capture animation.
-Now, we'll need a volun--
-HOMER: Pick me! Pick me!
Now, when you move any part of your body,
our furry friend will copy you exactly.
Mmm... Hmm... (chuckles)
♪ I'm a little teapot short and stout ♪
♪ Here is my handle, here is my spout ♪
(grunting and moans)
(applause and laughing)
Uh, let me see.
(as Don Corleone) I'll make him
an offer he can't refuse.
(as Edith Ann) And that's the truth.
(blows raspberry)
-(humming)
-(laughing and applause)
That dog's a riot.
Thank you.
Don't spay or neuter your pets.
Good night!
(humming)
-HOMER: Zipperoonie.
-(Homer unzips zipper)
(moaning) Oh, yeah.
Urinal cake eroding.
Eroding, eroding... Gone!
(cheers and applause)
(embarrassed groaning)
That motion-capture suit is
just what this country needs.
Just think of all the hilarious motions
that are going uncaptured, like this.
(grunting)
See? Now wouldn't you love
to see that move
performed by a cartoon possum?
An opossum capering around like that
would be a smash hit.
That would be the world's
funniest marsupial.
You're right. That suit gizmo
could be worth billions.
And I'm going to get
a piece of the action.
-(car door closes)
-(tires screeching)
So, does he still work here, or what?
I'd like to withdraw my life savings,
please. And hurry!
Uh, sir, this is a joint account.
Uh, you'll need
your wife's signature, too.
Oh! Yes, of course.
Uh, she's behind that plant.
Hello, Marge.
(as Marge) Hi, Homie.
(as Homer) Sign this, please.
(as Marge) You're the boss.
(as Lisa) Daddy, ask the man
for some candy.
(as Homer) No, no. No candy for you.
(as Lisa) Well, at least
get some candy for yourself.
(chuckling) Kids.
(sighs)
Here's your candy.
So long, sucker!
Uh, sir, your life savings.
Uh, yes, I see that it's in bill form.
Excellent.
I'd like to buy 500 shares
of Animotion Incorporated.
OK. Uh, now before I execute this order,
are you sure you understand
the risks of stock ownership?
Absolutely.
ALL: ♪ We're in the money ♪
♪ We're in the money ♪
(roaring)
You heard the monkey. Make the trade.
-(phone ringing)
(voice on phone)
For automated stock prices,
please state the company name.
-Animotion.
-Animotion,
up one and one-half.
-Yahoo!
-Yahoo, up six and a quarter.
Huh? What is this crap?
(voice on phone)
Fox Broadcasting, down eight.
Sleep tight, my beloved.
You're my ticket out of this hellhole.
-Homer!
-Sorry.
Our ticket out of this hellhole.
Turning to the stock market,
Animotion is up an eighth...
-Yes!
-...after plunging
75 points this morning.
Oh, I hope plunging means up
and 75 means 200.
The firm declared super-duper bankruptcy,
which is terrible news for the company's
only stockholder, Homer Simpson.
Oh!
-(cowbell ringing)
-HOMER: Family meeting!
Family meeting!
OK, people, let's keep this short.
We all want to get home to our families.
-(all chuckle)
-All right, first item,
I lost our life savings
in the stock market.
Now, let's move on to the real issue,
Lisa's hogging of the maple syrup.
Well, maybe if Mom didn't
make such dry waffles.
There, I said it.
Well, maybe if you ate some meat
you'd have a natural lubricant.
(gasps) You lost all our money?
Point of order,
I didn't lose all the money.
There was enough left for this cowbell.
Damn you, eBay!
I have a great way
to solve our money woes.
You rent your womb
to a rich, childless couple.
If you agree,
signify by getting indignant.
Are you crazy? I'm not going to be
a surrogate mother.
Come on, Marge. We're a team.
It's uter-us, not uter-you.
-Forget it.
-Hmm.
You know, Homer, I got
a great way to make money.
I'm a human guinea pig.
You mean, like medical testing?
Yeah, medical, military, chewing stuff.
-Chewing stuff?
-Yeah,
like you chew on a telephone wire
till you get a shock.
Oh, oh, right. OK.
Yeah, but aren't
those experiments dangerous?
Ah, you get a few side effects.
-Are those ears?
-Ow! Not so loud!
Hmm...
First, we'll test this
experimental perfume on you.
It burns! It burns!
-(screaming)
-Hmm...
-We'll call it "Desert Breeze."
-ALL: Mm-hmm.
(humming)
That appetite suppressant is amazing.
Homer, you really have
no desire to eat that food?
Food? I'm blind!
(screaming)
Who's going to buy a pill
that makes you blind?
We'll let marketing worry about that.
(grunting)
(beeping, buzzing)
D'oh!
Where did that rat come from?
He must have brought it in with him.
-Hmm...
-(buzzes)
Damn it.
Man, is he dumb.
Where do they get these subjects?
He's a little too well-fed to be a wino.
Hey, what's that?
Zoom in on section eight.
Rotate 20 degrees.
(beeping)
(both gasping)
Mr. Simpson, I'm afraid you have a crayon
lodged in your brain.
There's a crayon in my brain?
But I've had thousands of head x-rays.
How come no one ever noticed it before?
Oh, I can answer that.
You see, whenever I pick up an x-ray,
I always hold it like this.
My thumb must have covered up
the crayon every time.
(chuckling)
I'll show myself out.
Do you have any idea
how this might have happened?
Well, I'm not sure,
but it might have happened
when I was six.
Fourteen,
fifteen,
sixteen!
Whoo-hoo!
Oh, I don't feel so good.
(sneezing)
Uh, I think that's all of them.
Mr. Simpson, this could be responsible
for your subnormal intelligence.
Hey, I came here to be drugged,
electrocuted and probed, not insulted.
We could remove the crayon for you.
It could vastly increase your brain power,
or it could possibly kill you.
Hmm... increase my killing power, eh?
Let's do it.
-(vehicle approaching)
-(tires screeching)
Oh, Homer, where have you been?
I just underwent a procedure
to increase my IQ 50 points.
-Really?
-And they gave me
this spiffy nerd ensemble, too.
Do you feel smarter?
Is the capital of North Dakota Bismarck?
It is.
I don't believe it.
Say something else smart.
Dr. Joyce Brothers may be well known,
but her psychological
credentials are highly suspect.
It's true!
-Oh!
-(all gasping)
Now, who's up for a trip
to the library tomorrow?
Notice I no longer say
"liberry" or "tomorry."
I'd love to go to the library with you.
It's a date.
Dad, did you read all these books today?
Everything from Hop on Pop
to Death Be Not Proud.
It's so tragic the way they hopped on Pop.
I always dreamed
you'd be my library buddy.
-Get out.
-No, really.
I think books have an amazing
power to bring people together.
Look, even Cletus is checking one out.
Now, hold still.
Nothing cracks a turtle like Leon Uris.
Ow! Dang it! Ow!
-(piano sonata ending)
-ANNOUNCER: That sonata may not be
a Glenn Gould performance,
but I must say it's "good as Gould."
(laughing)
Hey, Flanders, heading for church?
Well, I thought I could
save you a little time.
Ooh, found a new shortcut?
Better. I was working
on a flat tax proposal
and I accidentally proved there's no God.
We'll just see about that.
Uh-oh. Well, maybe he made a mistake.
Nope, it's airtight.
Can't let this little doozy get out.
(whistling "Hark! The Herald Angels Sing")
Welcome to the third lecture in our series
on "not putting things up your nose."
Please welcome Homer Simpson.
(sparse applause)
I am here to give hope to the least of you
because we all have a crayon up our nose.
Maybe it's not a crayon made of wax.
-Maybe it's a crayon made of prejudice.
-Question.
-Yes, Nelson.
-A moron says what?
Not being a moron, I wouldn't know.
However... (mumbling)
-What?
-Ladies and gentlemen,
I give you your moron.
-(groans)
-(jeering laughter)
You see, it's cool to be smart.
So be like me, and use your minds.
Paint a painting, sing a song,
and dance a dance.
(cheering)
Thank you. Unfortunately,
due to budget cuts,
we are canceling art, music and dance.
Please evacuate the auditorium
before it's bulldozed into a mini-mall.
-(rumbling)
-(screaming)
So... is that your usual coffee mug?
-Yup.
-Huh. Looks a little bigger.
-It's not.
-(Homer humming)
Whatcha mailing, Homer?
I've compiled a thorough
safety report on this plant.
How come you're not
giving it to Mr. Burns?
I've decided to disintermediate
the local authorities
and send it straight to
the Nuclear Regulatory Commission.
Yeah, and just in time.
Every day there's more skin on my pillow.
Yeah, it's nice to have
someone with brains
in this nuclear plant.
Homer's the guy who rigged up my pants
with this special codpiece.
-Comfy, isn't it?
-Oh, yeah.
It provides the freedom and protection
I so sorely need.
-(chuckles) Yeah!
-Yeah!
It seems the federales
have been tipped off
by an anonymous whistle-blower.
Mm-hmm.
Now, while the plant
is brought up to code,
-there will be massive layoffs.
-(all gasping)
That is to say, total layoffs.
Toodles.
(indistinct chatter)
(tires squealing)
(groans) Way to put us
out of work, genius.
I can't feed my family with a codpiece.
Hey, you can't hate me.
I'm your better.
Your better!
Ooh, you've really done it
this time, dum-dum.
(moans)
MEN (chanting): Burn! Burn! Burn!
Burn! Burn! Burn!
Effigy, eh?
Yeah, nothing burns like an effigy.
Hey, that's me.
Stop that.
The fire inspector would be appalled.
Don't tell me how to feel. (grunts)
So, you all hate me?
That's right, brainiac.
You cost us our jobs,
which we need for working.
Not to mention driving to.
And I was a lot happier
before I knew Dame Edna was a man.
A lot happier.
You ain't welcome here
no more, smart boy.
Hmm. I'm detecting a distinct strain
of anti-intellectualism
in this tavern-- Ah!
Power off, Einstein.
Lisa, why didn't you warn me?
Being a brain has alienated me
from all my friends.
Dad, as intelligence goes up,
happiness often goes down.
In fact, I made a graph.
I make a lot of graphs.
Well, what gets you through the day?
Oh, many things, tai chi, chai tea.
But I find, when I can't keep the unhappy
thoughts from swirling in my brain,
the best thing is
usually a nice, long walk.
A walk? That's a really good idea.
Hmm? Hmm...
(all laughing)
Do you take this woman
to be your lawfully wedded wife?
BOTH: I do.
One groom...
Two grooms?
But he...
But you can't...
Oh, my medication.
(groans)
Radical.
Is that your final answer?
(laughing)
I don't understand.
That wasn't funny.
Wait a minute.
Somebody's not laughing here.
-It's him.
-Hey, don't blame me.
This movie is tired and predictable.
You know she's going to
wind up marrying Richard Gere.
(all gasping)
I thought she'd wind up
with that rich snob.
Ably played by Bill Paxton.
It's Bill Pullman, you fool! Ah!
Point out your plot holes elsewhere.
Is there no place for the man
with the 105 IQ?
I'm a Spaulding Gray in a Rick Dees world.
Change me back to the blissful boob I was.
I'm sorry, we don't play God here.
That's ridiculous.
You do nothing but play God.
And I think your octoparrot would agree.
(squawks) Polly shouldn't be. (whistles)
Look, what if we gave you the name
of an unlicensed surgeon?
Oh, that would be heaven.
(stutters) "Moe Szyslak"?
MOE: That's right. I'm a surgeon.
So what do you want here?
Appendectomy? Lipo?
Or... the sampler?
That's very popular.
I want you to stick this crayon
into my brain.
No problem.
The ol' Crayola oblongata.
Ah. Now for a little powder blue.
Oh, no. He wouldn't.
All right. Tell me when I hit
the sweet spot.
Deeper, you pusillanimous pilsener-pusher.
All right, all right.
Defense! Uh! Uh! Defense! Uh! Uh!
Uh, that's pretty dumb, but, uh...
Extended warranty?
How can I lose?
Perfect.
Sweetheart, a missing crayon
could be anywhere.
Who wants lottery tickets?
OK, it's in his brain.
Dad, how could you?
We were connecting
in such a meaningful way.
We were what-what in a what-what?
(sighs)
Yeah, which reminds me, I need a sandwich.
Hey, what's this?
I don't know. Must be something
I wrote before Moe fixed me.
"Lisa, I'm taking the coward's way out,
but before I do, I just want you to know,
being smart made me appreciate
how amazing you really are."
-(munching loudly)
-Oh, Dad.
Huh?
Oh, you want a hug.
Well, that I know how to do.
-(grunting and chomping loudly)
-Mmm.
Mmm... ug.
(closing theme playing)
Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services