CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme music playing)
(bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(jazzy solo)
(chimes)
(tires screech)
(honking horn)
D-oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
Woof.
Hey, open up!
I've been standing here
all morning.
Hey, Homer.
What are you doing at work?
The plant's closed
for fumigation.
(humming)
Uh-oh!
(panicked gasping)
Ohh...
No one told me
the plant was closed.
Didn't you get the e-mail?
What's an e-mail?
It's a computer thing
like an electric letter.
Or a quiet phone call.
I don't have a computer.
(laughs)
Too bad.
That's why you're at work
while we're living it up
on our day off.
Hey, Karl,
turn up the car radio.
Why not?
Anything goes today.
(swing music playing on radio)
That does it.
I'm getting a computer...
as soon as somebody
lets me out of here.
(rattling)
Oh. (chuckles) I'm so stupid.
Um, I guess I'll take that one.
Do you need a paperweight?
Because if you buy that machine
that's all you're going to have
is an expensive paperweight.
Well, a paperweight
would be nice
but what I really need
is a computer.
How about that one?
Mm-hmm. That technology
is three months old.
Only suckers buy
out-of-date machines.
Uh, you're not a sucker,
are you, sir?
Heavens, no.
Oh, good. Because if you were,
I'd ask you to leave the store.
I just need something
to receive e-mail.
(whistles)
You'll need a top-of-the-line
machine for that.
That's the same computer
astronauts use
to do their taxes.
I was an astronaut.
Of course you were.
Hmm.
$5,000?
You only have ten seconds
to decide, sir.
(whimpering)
This is the best computer
in the world
and always will be, right?
Absolutely.
Just run the deed to your house
through here.
ELECTRONIC VOICE:
You are on your
(male computerized voice)
...fifth...
(female computerized voice)
...mortgage.
(nervous laugh)
Hey, Lisa.
Check out my new computer.
Dad, you shouldn't drag
that around.
(laughs)
That's right, top of the line.
(screams, groans)
Stupid pothole.
Don't worry, head.
The computer
will do our thinking now.
Oh, yeah, perfect.
Now, then, computer,
kill Flanders.
Did I hear my name?
My ears are burning.
Good start.
Now finish the job.
Oh, you're busy.
Catch you later, compu-tater.
Oh, $5,000 for a computer
and it can't handle
a simple assignment.
(grunting)
(whines)
Dad, I'll set up your computer.
Why don't you and Bart
go play in the backyard?
You're it.
(laughter)
(Bart groans)
(laughter continues)
-HOMER: Why you little!
-(grunting)
OK, you're ready to go.
I've written down
the basic commands
so that anyone
can understand them.
Hmm...
-(flies buzzing)
-MARGE: Homer,
bring that back in the house.
HOMER: Fine.
(electronic beep)
Ooh, it's dancing Jesus.
♪ Dee, dee, dee, dee, dee ♪
If there's a better use
for the Internet
I haven't found it.
If you've committed a crime
and you want to confess
click "yes."
Otherwise, click "no."
You have chosen "no"
meaning you've committed a crime
but don't want to confess.
-A paddy wagon...
-(siren wails)
...is now speeding to your home.
Hey!
While you wait... why not buy
a police cap or t-shirt?
You have the right
to remain fabulous.
-(beeping)
-Here it is, everybody.
The world's greatest website.
(fanfare music plays)
-Dah, dah, dah, dah, dah...
-Hello, hello, hello, hello...
You'd think all the noises
would be annoying
but they're not.
I got suspended
from school today.
No kidding?
What do you think
of my page, Lisa?
Be honest.
It's great, isn't it?
Go ahead
and say it's great
if you want to.
They found a switchblade
in my locker.
Well, a web page is supposed
to be a personal thing.
You've just stolen copyrighted
material from everyone else.
They can sue you for that.
I took a swing at a cop.
They can't sue me
if they don't know who I am.
I'll just call myself Mr. X.
-(keyboard clacking)
-(electronic beep)
I'm just mad all the time.
Yup, you can't
go wrong with Mr. X.
Mom wants you to come to bed.
I can't. My web page
hasn't gotten a single hit.
(alarm rings)
Come on.
You have to offer
people something...
a joke, an opinion, an idea.
That lousy pothole.
Why don't they fix it?
I heard Mayor Quimby
spent the street repair fund
on a secret swimming pool
for himself.
-Get out. Who told you that?
-Nelson.
Ooh, that's the kind of dirt
that belongs on my web page.
You can't post that
on the Internet.
You don't even know
if it's true.
Nelson has never steered me
wrong, honey.
Nelson is gold.
You know,
it might have been Jimbo.
Beautiful.
We have confirmation.
(groaning)
Hmm.
Let's see here.
X-rated girls...
already bookmarked...
Dial "X" for sex.
Mr. X?
Hmm, shall I cross
the final frontier?
(electronic beeping)
What's this?
"Stolen funds?
Pothole money used
for swimming pool"?
There's no emoticon
for what I'm feeling.
Our Mayor's corrupt?
Oh, Mr. X has done this town
a great service
despite his poor grammar
and spelling.
WOMAN: Seymour, are you looking
at naked ladies?
No, Mother.
WOMAN: You sissy.
(groaning)
What's all this about
a secret swimming pool?
Uh, well, what secret
swimming pool is that?
Hey, let's look
behind that door.
QUIMBY: Don't go in there.
(all gasp)
(indistinct chatter)
Good lord, we've discovered
the ruins of an ancient city.
OK, you do better.
I did it.
I changed the world.
Now I know exactly
how God feels.
You want turkey sausage or ham?
Bring me two of every animal.
(mews)
A new Internet watchdog
is creating a stir
in Springfield.
Mr. X, if that is his real name,
has come up
with a sensational scoop.
Darn tootin'.
But we must never forget
that the real news
is on local TV
delivered by real,
officially licensed newsmen
like me, Kent Brockman.
Coming up,
how do they get those dogs
to talk on the beer commercials?
Cowboy Steve will tell you.
I'm happy you got
the potholes filled
but it's still irresponsible
to present rumors as facts.
Maybe you should quit
while you're ahead.
No way. Mr. X is going
to keep on digging and probing
until every person
in this town is in jail.
Argh! A coconut bagel!
Like poison, it tastes.
All right,
I'll tell you a secret.
My bagels are nothing
but week-old doughnuts.
Aw, who am I
to point the finger?
I once ran over a guy
in a parking lot
and dumped the body
on a golf course.
What a bombshell.
CHIEF WIGGUM:
In the interest of public safety
we have confiscated every
doughnut, bagel, cruller
and bear claw in the city.
And some coffee.
(slurping)
This morning, Mr. X reported
that your own department--
I know, I know, but I assure you
the police do not take prisoners
out of their cells
and race them... anymore.
What about using the electric
chair to cook chicken?
Yeah, uh,
this press conference is over.
-Wait. I have one more.
-No, it's over, Phil. It's over.
KENNY: According to my uncle
Miss Springfield
isn't as beautiful as she seems.
Word is, she uses
appearance-altering cosmetics?
-Oh, my God.
-That's shocking.
The public should be warned.
I wish Mr. X were here.
Oh, I don't know, Carl.
He might be closer
than you think.
Are you him?
-Are you Mr. X?
-No.
But you talk
in that real sly voice.
Hey, hey, everybody!
Homer's Mr. X.
I am not.
Or am I?
Are you?
No!
Well, if Mr. X were here
right now
I'd buy him a tall frosty.
Hey, Moe, can you keep a secret?
-No.
-Not even a little one?
-What if I just whisper it?
-No, I tells you.
-Oh!
♪ I've been sitting
on the toilet ♪
♪ All the live-long day ♪
BURNS: Is everything ready for
the secret meeting, Smithers?
SMITHERS: Yes, sir.
I hope no one
finds out about this.
It's pure journalistic dynamite.
Uh... sir, this place
could be bugged. Shh!
(dryer whirring)
OK, now we can talk.
(gasping)
Turn it off!
(groans)
Journalistic dynamite.
(gasps)
(speaking indistinctly)
Then it's agreed.
I'll supply you terrorists
with deadly uranium.
You are a credit
to the great Satan.
Oh, pshaw!
(humming)
HOMER: I love spying.
(groans)
Oh, don't worry
about those fumes.
They'll be sucked
into that air vent.
HOMER: Ohh!
This place is falling apart.
"And who's selling the uranium
to the terrorists?
Mmm?
Mm-hmm. "Montgomery Burns."
Now we wait.
(groans) Let go of me!
I'm innocent.
Whoa. He's in trouble.
We'd like to award this year's
Pulitzer Prize to Mr. X.
(cheering and applauding)
Unfortunately,
we don't know who he is
so his cash award will be used
to feed starving children.
No!
Move! Move!
I'm Mr. X! Gimme! Gimme!
(clamoring)
We'll need some proof.
Ta-da!
He is Mr. X. Hah!
Thank you, folks.
And now I'm off
to expose more secret
conspiracies and...
Ooh! Oh, I bit my tongue!
MARGE: I'm proud that
you won the Pulitzer.
Finally.
But I do feel bad
about the starving children.
They're with God now.
Oh. Well, that's good.
Oh.
Hey, guys, how's it going?
Oh, don't worry
about the Mr. X thing.
I'm just here for a beer.
(hesitates)
Uh, I don't know if I want you
in here no more, Homer.
I got a lot of secrets
I'd prefer to keep clandestine.
Terrible, disturbing secrets.
MAN: ...so hungry.
I smell another Pulitzer.
Yikes!
Well, Helen, as it says
in the Bible...
-I'll tell you later.
-Mmm.
Oh, nobody's visiting
my web page anymore.
My counter
is actually going down.
(wind blows)
Well, you can't post news
if you don't have any.
That's a great idea.
I'll make up some news.
(shudders) At least take off
your Pulitzer Prize
when you say that.
(humming)
-Let's see now.
-(growls)
"Bulletin-- New race discovered
living six inches under Denver."
Oh, Dad.
"All named Morton."
Or... "Mortonson."
This Mr. X says
Spanish and Italian
are the same language.
(exhales deeply)
Well, that's surprising.
They're controlling our minds
with flu shots.
I knew it.
Well, kids, now aren't you glad
we don't believe
in inoculations?
BOTH (shivering): Yeah.
Mommy?
Hey, Mr. X, I got a tip for you.
In science class,
they're dissecting frozen hoboes
and I have the bindles
to prove it.
Real news is great, son,
but I'm getting 1,000 hits
an hour with grade-A bull plop.
(bell chimes)
Give me 100 lotto tickets, Apu,
because Mr. X is on a roll.
(groans) Stop it, Apu.
You're scaring me.
(whining)
What's going on?
Help! I'm being kidnapped!
(humming)
(muffled talking)
(muffled)
Whoo! (sighs)
This is not a library. Whoo!
HOMER: Save me, Mr. X!
Wait. I'm Mr. X. (groans)
(Homer groaning)
(bird squawking)
Huh? Whuzza?
-(squawks)
-Hmm, hmm.
(birds calling)
(peacock squawking)
What the hell?
How did I get here?
What is this place?
This is the island.
How do I get out of here?
Oh, no one leaves the island.
So I'm a prisoner? How come?
Because you know something.
But I don't know anything.
At least I don't think I do.
See you tomorrow.
No, you won't!
Hello, operator?
I'd like to report
a really weird island.
Please send lots of rescue
'copters to...
(hissing)
(groggily)
Oh, well, all right. Whatever.
(thuds)
(snickers)
(groans)
Welcome, friend. I'm Number Six.
I'm number 15.
What number are you?
I am not a number.
I am a man
and don't you ever...
Oh, wait, I'm Number Five.
Ha-ha, in your face, Number Six!
Yes, well done.
Who are all these oddballs?
Well, they keep us here
because we know too much.
Number 27 there knows how
to turn water into gasoline.
Number 12 knows the deadly
secret behind Tic-Tacs
and I invented
the bottomless peanut bag.
Wow!
So, who brought us here?
I don't know.
-Did you bring us here?
-No.
Don't worry.
If even half of your
husband is out here
Officer Scraps will find him.
Oh, that's a darling
name for a dog.
(barks)
(barking)
Yep, he's on the trail,
all right.
-Uh-oh.
-(barking frantically)
Better go fish him out, Lou.
OK, Chief.
Uh, the shoes are
part of the uniform.
Right, Chief.
(groans)
Oh, they drugged the tea.
They knew my one weakness.
(hydraulic whirring)
Hello, Number Five.
How's every little thing?
Who are you and why are
you holding me here?
I want answers now
or I want them eventually!
Fair enough.
I'll level with you.
(groans)
Ow. Please, don't do that.
-Sorry.
-I'll be blunt.
Your web page has
stumbled upon our secret plan.
That's impossible.
All my stories are bull plop.
Bull plop!
Don't be cute.
I'm referring
to the flu shot expose.
You see, we're the ones
loading them
with mind-controlling additives.
But why? (grunts)
To drive people
into a frenzy of shopping.
That's why flu shots are given
just before Christmas.
Of course.
It's so simple.
Wait. No, it's not.
It's needlessly complicated.
Yes, it is.
And we can't have you out there
mucking it up, now, can we?
No, sir.
There's a good boy.
Let's get you some ice cream.
There we are.
Look, you can drug me
all you want
but my family won't rest
till they find
my drug-bloated corpse.
I wouldn't count on that,
Number Five.
As far as your family knows
Homer Simpson is walking
in the front door
right about now.
I'm sorry. What?
(humming fretfully)
(gasps) Homie!
(German accent) Marge, honey,
fraulein, I'm home.
You're not my husband.
Jah, please forgive
my unexplained two-week absence.
To make it up to you
we will go out to dinner
at a sensibly priced restaurant
then have a night
of efficient German sex.
Well, I sure don't
feel like cooking.
(hissing)
Oh...
(buzzing)
Aren't there any evil movies on?
Maybe something
about an evil island?
There's something really
different about you, Dad.
I am a new tie wearing.
Oh, yeah.
(Homer groaning)
I'm tired of being
drugged and gassed.
There's got to be a way
to escape.
-Psst.
-Huh?
I've worked on this
for 33 years.
It's made out of
toilet paper rolls
toothpicks and plastic forks.
And the sail is made
of scabs and dynamite.
It's small and it's smelly
but it should carry
both of us to...
-(groans)
-Whoo-hoo!
Tha-that's the third time
that's happened.
Oh, no, an anti-escape orb!
(groans)
(grunts)
Huh. That was easy.
Why did you think
a big balloon would stop people?
Shut up, that's why!
Ooh! What a horrible
four months!
Now to warn everybody.
Attention, some crazy creeps
on an island somewhere
are secretly running the world.
-Hey!
-Sorry, old chap
but you're proving
quite the caterpillar
in our buttermilk.
-Huh?
-We're shutting you down.
Not a chance.
No one can silence me but me.
That arranged can be.
Wha...?
(gasps)
(gagging)
Yes, fight and struggle.
(grunts)
If I know me, he won't like
being kicked in the crotch.
(in German) Gott im Himmel!
(in English) Oh, Marge, it's me,
The real Homer.
Oh, Homie!
Mmm-mm.
(slow clapping)
Bravo, Number Five.
But you know what happens
to bad little fishies
who wriggle through the net?
Can I turn this off?
-Absolutely.
-Hey!
Nice to have you back, Homer.
(barking)
The dog thinks so, too.
(all laughing)
"The dog thinks..."
(all groaning)
Bad dog.
(laughing gaily)
Once you get used
to the druggings
this isn't a bad place.
Oh, it's wonderful.
Truly God's country.
(snickers)
(hissing)
HOMER (sinisterly):
See you on the island.
LISA (robotically):
Yes, the island.
(theme music playing)
Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services