(rattling)
(woman yells)
Kids...
(boy screaming) Mom! Mom!
Kevin!
(cries out in pain)
Mom! Mom! Mom!
Mom! Mom!
Mom! Ruby's gone!
Ruby?
Ruby!
(Blevins) Agent Mulder's latest 302.
Requesting assignment
and travel expenses for the both of you.
Sioux City, Iowa.
That's the first I've heard of it.
It came up through channels, from Mulder's
ASAC to the District G-14, then my desk.
I don't understand.
(Blevins)
In essence, Mulder wants the Bureau...
...to assign a case number
to a tabloid headline.
- He must have more evidence than...
- Not according to his 302.
I admit, that is strange.
Even for Mulder.
Perhaps it has something to do with this.
Take a look.
An X-File?
Has he shared this with you?
There's no need to protect him.
He initiated the file himself.
She was his sister.
She disappeared 21 years ago. He was...
...12 and she was 8.
He claims that he was in the room
when it happened.
He recalls a...
bright light outside the window and...
...a presence in the room.
In your opinion,
has Agent Mulder's personal agenda
clouded his professional judgement?
In my opinion, no.
But you can see
how it might appear that way?
As you know...
...Mulder's preoccupation
with fringe matters
has been a source of friction in the Bureau.
This is another case in point.
I'm going to disallow the 302.
With respect, sir,
at least let me talk with him
and make a recommendation.
It just doesn't seem substantial enough
to warrant an investigation.
So we disagree.
It's not the first time, it won't be the last.
- If we had a legitimate source...
- This is the essence of science.
Ask an impertinent question,
you're on your way to a pertinent answer.
What makes this case any more credible
than the 100-year-old mother
with the lizard baby?
Because the lizard baby wasn't born
anywhere near Lake Okobogee.
Oko-what?
Bogee.
Okobogee.
Is that supposed to mean something to me?
If you know anything about trout fishing.
Or UFO hot spots.
(Scully) Define hot spot.
Four sightings in 1967, August, including
one by a National Weather Service plane.
This is a light-blasted
digitally-enhanced enlargement.
The pilot took that?
Try a Girl Scout with an Instamatic.
Four girls said they saw something.
Five, including the Den Mother.
The Air Force said it was a weather balloon.
But no weather balloon was launched
that day within 700 miles.
Now read me the names
of those Girl Scouts from 1967.
Lisa Terrel, Bonnie Winston,
Doreen McCallister, Darlene Mor...
(Mulder) It's the same Darlene Morris.
Darlene Morris? I'm Agent Scully
and this is Agent Fox Mulder.
We talked with you on the phone last night.
Please come in.
Well, I knew that if I screamed loud and long
enough that someone would listen.
But I never expected the FBI.
This is Kevin. Kevin...
...say hi.
Would you like some coffee?
Some days I can't even...
...get myself up out of bed.
And Kevin has been acting so strange.
I don't know what to do any more.
I just want her back again.
(Scully) Ms Morris...
...during the divorce,
was there a custody battle?
Charles had nothing to do with this.
How can you be so sure?
Because I know what happened.
It's just like it was before.
- Summer of 1967? The Girl Scout troop?
- How did you know about that?
Your name's on record at the Center
for UFO Studies in Evanston, Illinois.
Really?
A pilot made a similar sighting
over the same area on the same day.
They took her, didn't they?
You... you said that, um,
Kevin was there the night it happened?
He didn't see anything. He was asleep.
Can I talk to him anyway?
(Mulder) Thanks.
You know...
...I've told this story so many times now.
Oh, to the newspapers and the police.
And every time I tell it,
people get this... look in their eye.
Just like the look that you've got right now.
Hey, buddy.
Mind if I sit down?
Thanks.
Your mom tells me
you've been having nightmares.
I guess so.
- You wanna tell me about 'em?
- No.
All right.
What are you doing?
Are you making something?
Can I take a look at it?
Thanks.
It's coming from there.
The TV?
(Mulder) Maybe it's a binary sequence.
Could be anything, could be nothing.
I know you're busy.
Look, I know a friend who knows a friend
who can get you a ticket
to 3 Redskins game.
You got it!
All right. You know where to find me?
Thanks, Danny.
So, as I was telling your partner,
we found no evidence of kidnap.
No phone call, no ransom note.
- And since we have no body...
- (Mulder) You assumed she ran away?
It wouldn't be the first time
Ruby ran away from home.
How do you explain what her mother saw?
I think Darlene
has a very active imagination.
I've heard those stories since first grade.
So, basically, you ignored her statement.
I included it in my report.
But you didn't bother to check it out.
We found nothing at the campsite.
Let me tell you something.
Darlene's little girl was no prom queen.
I can't count the number of times
I pulled her out of parked cars...
...or found her puking her guts out.
- It was just a matter of time...
- Before what?
Before something bad happened. If Darlene
makes up stories to get past that, fine.
But don't tell me it's the truth.
I'm not gonna waste my time.
(Scully) I just think it's a good idea
not to antagonise local law enforcement.
Who, me? I'm Mr Congeniality.
We might need his help one of these days.
I'll send him a Bundt cake.
(girl) You're looking for Ruby, right?
That's right.
Who are you?
Doesn't matter.
Are you a friend of Ruby's?
Ruby didn't have friends.
She just had people she liked to hang with.
And she liked to hang out with you?
I guess we had some times.
- Like the night she disappeared?
- It was Greg.
She was supposed to see him that night.
- Who's Greg?
- Her boyfriend, Greg Randall.
Supposed to meet up at the lake.
They had stuff to talk about.
What kind of stuff?
Greg got Ruby pregnant.
Whatever. She got herself pregnant.
Do you know
what they were planning to do about it?
They were gonna leave town.
At least that's what Ruby told me.
You know Greg from school?
Greg? School?
I don't think so.
All he ever did since we met him
was pour beer. The Pennsylvania Pub.
(books fall)
(heavy rock music)
Excuse me! Do you know
where we can find Greg Randall?
Who's asking?
What kind of trouble's he in now?
We were hoping you could tell us.
Greg called in sick three weeks ago.
I haven't heard from him since.
Any ideas where he might have gone?
No, but if you find him, tell him he's fired.
This is our hotel if you hear of anything.
That's a nice tattoo. What is that?
What's it look like?
A flying saucer.
You don't believe that stuff, do you?
I take it you don't?
No, I think it's just a bunch of crazy people
howling at the moon.
So, you haven't been out
to Lake Okobogee, have you?
No, I haven't. Why?
You should ride with us some time.
You might see some things
that'd change your mind.
Get a killer sunburn
in the middle of the night.
(chuckles)
(whispering)
(man) Where's Mulder?
Where did you get the document?
If you explain what you're talking about,
maybe I can help.
This is a document?
It just looks like
a bunch of ones and zeros to me.
- Tell me where you got it.
- Tell me what it is.
Keep playing games
and you'll be facing the D6.
You can explain to them
why you're obstructing justice.
It's your call, Holtzman.
But I'm not accountable to anybody
outside my sub-committee.
I don't care if it's the NSA
or the Vatican police.
It's a defence satellite transmission.
You're kidding!
A fragment, but highly classified.
We need to know where it came from.
Well, sure.
I'll let you know as soon as I find out.
You just bought yourself
a one-way back to Washington.
(conversation on mobile phone)
We got it.
(Mulder) Great.
What?
You shouldn't have told 'em.
They have no jurisdiction.
Mulder, they're NSA. They think
the boy's a threat to national security.
How can an 8-year-old boy who can barely
multiply be a threat to national security?
People call me paranoid.
How did Kevin obtain
top-secret information?
Where do you think he got it from?
Watch your step, ma'am.
It'll be OK, baby. Don't worry.
- It'll be OK.
- Come with me, son.
Mom!
It'll be all right, baby.
Watch your head, please.
You guys do really delicate work.
Let's get this to Cryptography.
I think we got what we needed. Thank you.
- What is it?
- I'm not sure.
- We scanned it through the mainframe.
- And none of the information is actionable?
Other than the satellite transmission,
none of it is a national security risk.
The boy's being released later.
So it was just a random set
of ones and zeros?
There was nothing random about it.
I don't understand.
All information can be rendered digitally
in a series of ones and zeros.
When we downloaded the data, we found
an amazing range of... Well, see for yourself.
Da Vinci's Universal Man.
A DNA double helix.
There's lots more.
(digital music)
That's the Brandenburg Concertos.
But they're just fragments. Some lines
from the Koran, a Shakespearean sonnet.
Like someone's switching channels?
- Mrs Morris?
- I have nothing to say to you.
Please, give me a minute to explain.
Would you please just wait
right over there for mama?
- I thought you were supposed to help us.
- (Scully) This has been a terrible mistake.
The government will pay
for all repairs and damages.
I don't want your money.
I want my daughter back.
And I want you to leave us alone.
But your son has seen something.
You stay away from me
and you stay away from my child.
(Darlene) Come on, honey.
It's OK. Let's go now.
I thought we were headed back into town.
Where are we going?
The boy is the key, Scully. I know it.
- The key to what?
- Finding Ruby.
Just think about it for a minute.
He's receiving digitised data
from a television screen.
Agent Atsumi
said it was a statistical aberration.
- I admit it's not much of an explanation...
- I think that Kevin is a conduit of some kind.
A conduit?
A link... or a connection to whoever...
...or whatever took Ruby that night.
But how?
If there was an abduction, it's likely
that Kevin was touched in some way.
Mulder, I know what you're thinking.
I know why this is so important to you.
I know!
But there is no evidence
indicating an abduction.
That's why we're going to Lake Okobogee.
(geese overhead)
According to the police photos,
Ruby and Kevin were sleeping right here.
A stone's throw from the forest wall.
Meaning what?
Meaning anybody could have
come out of the forest to grab her.
Have you noticed the tree line?
(Mulder) Evidence of extreme heat.
Or an electrical storm.
Besides which, there's nothing
to connect it to the night...
- ...of Ruby's disappearance.
- That's true.
Do you think lightning
could have caused this?
Do you have any idea at what
temperature sand solidifies into glass?
(Mulder) 2,500° Fahrenheit.
Something was out here. Something
hot enough to turn sand into glass.
To singe those trees
and to blister the roof of that camper.
(animal whining)
(whispers) Mulder!
Look!
(cocks gun)
What is it?
It's a grave. Shallow, by the smell of it.
What are you doing?
Mulder, you are disturbing a crime scene.
Stop!
What if it's her?
I need to know.
Are you OK, Mulder?
Fine.
Looks like a male Caucasian.
Sir.
Victim's name was Greg Randall.
Ruby's boyfriend.
Ruby had a lot of boyfriends.
- Can I take a look at that?
- Go right ahead.
Look at that.
It's her. The girl from the library.
Who?
We didn't get her name, but she claimed
Greg and Ruby had run off together.
Well, Doc Fowler's a buddy of mine.
Delivered both my kids.
I can find out who had that appointment.
(Scully) Have a seat, Tessa.
We know that you lied to us the other day.
We know that you had the appointment
with Dr Fowler on August 7th.
We know that you're pregnant, not Ruby.
- Then you don't know nothing.
- We can prove it, Tessa.
And we can prove that Greg...
was the father.
So what if he was the father?
(Scully) This is very serious.
Do you understand how serious this is?
(Scully) You've waived
the right to an attorney.
So if you lie to us here today...
...you could be charged with perjury.
(sighs)
He promised me
we'd be in LA by Christmas.
He had a friend there.
And I'd never seen the ocean.
You said he and Ruby
were seeing each other.
You said they were planning
to meet at the lake. Is that true?
Lookit, I was nowhere
near the lake that night, OK?
Sure you were, Tessa.
You knew they were meeting,
so you sat and you waited for them.
- You were angry and jealous.
- I wasn't.
You waited, and when they showed
you killed him first, isn't that how it went?
- No.
- You snuck up and you shot him in the back.
Barn!
And then you killed Ruby.
What was she doin' before she died?
Was she pleading for her life?
Was she running away?
I didn't kill her!
- Where's she buried?
- I don't know!
- You don't know where you buried her?
- I didn't kill her!
- You didn't?
- She wasn't even there that night!
Well, how would you know that, Tessa,
if you weren't there yourself?
You're not seeing the whole picture here.
- Which is?
- Which is that in all likelihood Ruby is dead.
Is that your conclusion
or the Sioux City Sheriff's Department's?
They're searching the National Park
and a dive team is going to drag the lake.
They're wasting their time.
Do you really think
Tessa is telling the truth?
Why not?
What if Ruby never did show up that night?
She lied to us in the library
and lied about her pregnancy.
Why wouldn't she lie about killing Ruby?
Because something was out there
in those woods!
We have a suspect in custody.
We have a confession to one murder...
...and a statement which speaks
to the intent to commit another.
It's over, Mulder. It's time
to turn this over to local law enforcement.
I can't do that.
Mulder, where are you going?
To talk to the boy.
- Darlene won't let you.
- I've gotta see him.
They don't want anything to do with us!
Mulder, stop! Stop running after your sister.
This won't bring her back.
Come with me or don't, but until they
find a body I'm not giving up on that girl.
(knocks) Hello?
Mrs Morris?
Kevin?
(kettle whistling)
Mulder?
(Scully) What does it mean?
I don't know.
I'm gonna check upstairs.
Oh, my God!
What is it?
Just come up here.
Look.
It's her!
It's Ruby.
This is a long shot. They could be anywhere.
You know, when I was a kid...
...I had this ritual.
I'd close my eyes
before I walked into my room.
Because I thought that one day when
I opened them my sister would be there.
Just lying in bed...
like nothing ever happened.
I'm still walking into that room.
Every day of my life.
Scully!
Daflene!
Look, there's a “ahead.
(woman shouts)
- Are you OK?
- It's here. I saw it.
- Where's Kevin?
- I couldn't keep up.
(Scully) Go ahead!
Kevin!
(rumbling)
(whooping)
- Are you OK?
- She's back!
Kevin, I'm sorry, but...
She's here. I know it!
Kevin, I don't think she is.
- I know you wanted it to be her. I did too.
- (Scully) Mulder!
Come on!
Scully?
(Kevin) Ruby!
She's unconscious but alive.
I'll get help.
She's been awake for almost an hour.
Any ideas what caused the coma?
No sign of head trauma, no narcotic traces
or electrolyte abnormalities.
But her white blood cell count was sky-high.
Any attendant reduction in the lymphocyte
population or release of glucocorticoids?
Um...
Actually, both. How did you know that?
They're symptoms
of prolonged weightlessness.
Shuttle astronauts have reported
similar imbalances.
(Scully) Hi.
Hi, Ruby.
Who are you?
We're with the FBI. I'm Special Agent
Dana Scully and this is Fox Mulder.
My mom said you might be coming by.
How are you feeling?
Fine, I guess.
(Mulder) Where were you, Ruby?
Can you tell us?
It's OK, Ruby. He knows.
I'm not supposed to tell.
They told me not to say.
Who told you?
Ruby, who told you?
Sweetheart, you don't have to say anything.
You're right. We should wait
till Ruby gets a little stronger.
Can we speak outside for a moment?
I think that it's best
that we put all of this behind us.
I mean,
hasn't Ruby been through enough already?
I know how disoriented she must seem
right now. But in a couple of weeks, we...
I don't want her talking to you. Or anyone.
She should be encouraged to tell her story.
It's important that you let her.
Important to who?
I have my daughter back.
I don't want more trouble.
Besides, she can't remember anything.
But she will remember one day,
even if it's only in dreams.
When she does, she'll want to talk about it.
She'll need to talk about it.
Like I did?
(Darlene) Listen to me.
I have been ridiculed for speaking my mind.
But it was the truth, Darlene.
It's caused me nothing but heartache.
I don't want the same thing for her.
It doesn't have to be that way for Ruby.
As far as I know, she spent the last month
on the back of a Harley-Davidson.
Is that what you'll tell Kevin?
I'm sorry.
- (voice on tape) Your eyes are open?
- (Mulder) Yeah, but it's like...
- ...nothing's happening.
- Try turning your head.
(Mulder) I can't.
- Why not?
- I don't know.
I can't move.
So I don't.
- I just lie there in bed.
- Can you see your sister?
No.
BUN can hear her.
- What does she say?
- She's calling out my name...
...over and over again.
She's crying out for help.
But I can't help her.
I can't move.
- Are you scared?
- I know I should be, but I'm not.
- Do you know why?
- Because of the voice.
- The voice?
- The voice in my head.
- What's it telling you?
- Not to be afraid.
It's telling me
that no harm will come to her.
And that one day she'll return.
Do you believe the voice?
(Mulder) I want to believe.