Roger your request for assistance,
50. What is your location?
Unit 50, go ahead.
Suspect now westbound.
Has entered the ship works off April Street.
Unit 50 still in pursuit. Over.
Unit 50, I copy. Keep me advised.
This is the police!
Pull your vehicle over and stop!
Stop your vehicle!
Put your hands on the hood and freeze!
Hold it!
On the ground! Do it!
You hear me?
- Face down! Do it!
- Stay there!
Agh!
Stop! Armed officer!
I hit him! I know I hit him!
Where the hell did he go?
He'll be bleeding bad.
The Lipari Island group off the coast of Italy.
But theirs is a very light lava, sir.
Exactly. But inside there must be something
the weight of the heaviest rock in existence.
But, Professor,
that would be Icelandic peridotite.
Precisely.
- There's a piece chipped off.
- By me.
What was the rock inside?
- Icelandic peridotite.
When I saw this I stopped chipping.
But how could a rock from Iceland...
Mulder.
Are you watching Channel 8?
..Across the world. What's your conclusion?
Science does notjump to conclusions.
It is not a guessing game.
..ship works, where a 60-mile
high-speed car chase ended this evening.
The suspect eluded capture
by leaping into the harbour...
..but not before reportedly
injuring several Ardis police officers.
Captain Roy LaCerio is standing by.
Captain...
..how did the man escape,
and how seriously injured were the officers?
Those details are still unclear.
I'll be talking to...
- We need you, Captain.
- You'll have to excuse me.
Captain Roy LaCerio being pulled away
during an intense manhunt.
during an intense...
Mulder, you've been through this tape
a hundred times.
What exactly are you hoping to find?
I don't know.
And all he told you was to watch Channel 8?
Yeah, that's all he said.
Do we even know why
the suspect was being chased?
As far as I can tell,
he wouldn't pull over for a moving violation.
That oughta put him
on the Ten Most Wanted list.
There's gotta be something here.
Some detail.
Something we're not seeing.
How do you know he's not yanking
your chain, this Deep Throat guy?
- Why would he do that?
- He has lied to you by his own admission.
He wouldn't call if there wasn't
something here I'm supposed to see.
Something he wants me to see.
Then what are you missing?
There were three different law
enforcement agencies out here last night.
Hunting a man on a moving violation?
It's not Silence of the Lambs,
but it's what we do.
The man in the photograph isn't wearing
a badge or uniform. He's not one of yours?
No, sir. But like I said, it was a zoo out here.
You said the suspect was shot.
Any explanation why the body
hasn't been recovered?
Well, we got our search ongoing.
Divers down there in shifts.
We're certain he will be found.
It's been almost 18 hours.
Where could the body be?
There are cables and debris all over
the bottom. This is a painstaking business.
Can I ask what the FBI's interest
in this case would be?
The suspect matches the description
of a federal fugitive...
Really? How's that? No description
of the suspect's been released.
If you don't mind,
can we take a look at the car, please?
It's been taken to the impound.
The report says that the car was registered
to a rental agency in Gaithersburg.
They had no idea that
the car was even missing.
You know, Mulder,
I think we're wasting our time here.
I don't know what the hell
I'm supposed to find.
You can't make out
the license plate in this photo.
Scully, look at this!
What?
Look at the car in the photo.
Look at the windshield.
It's not the same car.
It's called a caduceus.
It's sort of the adopted symbol
of the medical profession.
So probably only a doctor
would have that on his car.
Mm-hm.
I had the picture enhanced.
The plate is different.
3-AYF.
Fast forward.
That's all you can make out.
The rest is obscured.
Danny, it's Mulder.
I need you to run a Maryland plate.
All I got is a partial.
Registered to a doctor... or used to be.
Yeah, I'll hold.
- They switched cars on us and lied about it.
- Why would they do that?
Maybe the real owner of the car
has got something to hide.
- Dr Berube?
- Yes?
We're with the FBI.
Can we have a minute of your time?
- I'm actually very busy.
- I'm sorry.
Are you aware that a car registered to you
was involved in a high-speed chase in Ardis?
Excuse me?
- Doctor, do you own a silver Ciera?
- Uh, yes!
- It was used for what?
- A crime.
- Were you aware it was missing?
- Not until you mentioned it.
I have a housekeeper and she
often uses the car. It's a second car...
Please!
They should not be excited.
Nothing should be touched!
- I thought they were friendly.
- They're part of an experiment.
What kind of experiment?
- Am I under some kind of suspicion?
- No.
Then I think I've answered
all your questions.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have more work than time.
Thank you.
- Did he bite you?
- No, but he tried to.
It's almost five o'clock. We should check
with the housekeeper while we're here.
- No.
- No? What do you mean "no"?
I mean this has reached
the point of absurdity, Mulder.
We're here on half a hunch,
off of a cryptic phone call...
...chasing down a clue
that's based on speculation.
Well, that's all we've got.
That's all he's given us.
Who is this Deep Throat character?
We don't know anything about him,
what his name is, what he does...
His position is delicate.
He has access to information.
An indiscretion could expose him.
You don't know
this isn't just a game with him.
He's toying with you,
rationing out the facts.
You think he does it
because he gets off on it?
No.
I think he does it because you do.
Calling it a night, Mr Mulder?
My mother usually likes me home
before the streetlights come on.
- I'm surprised at you.
- Why?
- Your level of commitment has diminished.
- My level of commitment?
I'd have expected you to work all night
trying to put the pieces together.
Well, maybe if you'd given me
something more to work with...
- I've given you all I can.
- A news report?
- And where has it led you?
- Not very far.
It may be further than you realise.
You know, from day one
this has been on your terms.
I've gone along, been the dutiful son.
Maybe this time we can
cut the Obi-Wan Kenobi crap
and you can save me the trouble.
I fear you've become too dependent on me.
Let me tell you, I've got plenty to do
without chasing down your vague leads...
...or trying to decode your circular logic.
Maybe it's you who's become
too dependent on me...
...on my willingness to play your games.
- Mr Mulder?
- What?
Don't give up on this one.
Trust me. You've never been closer.
Closer to what?
Hello?
Who's there?
Working late tonight, Doctor?
What do you want here?
He's alive, isn't he?
- Has he contacted you?
- Please...
You're going to have to leave.
If you're from the FBI,
I've already answered your questions!
What questions?
I had nothing to say to them.
I have nothing to say to you.
Where's Dr Secare?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Please...
My work is very important.
I must get on with my work.
I'm afraid... your work is done.
- Anybody see anything?
- No.
Nothing.
I'm calling it off.
Get those guys out of the water.
Yes, sir. Shore to RC1.
Bring it in.
- There's nothing down there.
- Three days? Forget it.
The county sheriff's office
is conducting the investigation.
On the preliminary reports
it's listed as a suicide.
Suicide?
Yeah. They think that he trashed his lab
and then killed himself.
How?
Well, it says he tied one end of a roll
of medical gauze around his neck...
...and the other end to this gas outlet.
Then he jumped.
- I don't suppose there were any witnesses?
- Nope.
The man we met kept this place like he was
waiting for Good Housekeeping to show up.
I wouldn't have thought he'd do all this.
Or a Greg Louganis out the window.
I know. That gauze is troubling.
It's a bit too calculated, huh?
Almost as if someone
wanted to make doubly sure...
...he'd break his neck
before he hit the ground.
What else do we know about Dr Berube?
Um...
Terrence Allen Berube. Harvard Med, 1974.
He was working on the Human Genome
Project. Are you familiar with that?
Yeah, the mapping of all human genes.
Maybe the most ambitious scientific
endeavour in the history of mankind.
Right. But that's nothing extraordinary.
Thousands of scientists
were working on that project.
But only one who had a silver Ciera...
...and went bungee jumping
with gauze around his neck.
Sorry, I'm seeing the pieces,
but I'm not seeing the connection.
Maybe we're not seeing it because...
...it can't be seen. Not in any obvious way.
What do you think this is?
I don't know.
- Can you find out for me?
-  What are you gonna do?
See what else I can find out
about Dr Terrence Allen Berube.
OK, Mulder. But I'm warning you...
If this is monkey pee, you're on your own.
My first impression is
it's some kind of bacteria specimen.
Can I ask you where you got it?
It was recovered at a crime scene.
We've come a long way from
Colonel Mustard in the den with a rope!
I'm expecting it'll turn out to be nothing.
No!
No, you've definitely got something here.
Wow! Look at this!
What are they?
They're the size of bacteria,
but no bacteria I've seen.
How do you mean?
Well, most bacteria are
symmetrical and smooth. These are...
I don't know...
Strange.
- You can't identify them?
- Well, we could do a freeze fracture.
Take a thin slice off and see
what's going on inside these babies.
- If you don't mind waiting.
- No. No, I'll wait.
Hi, Danny. It's Mulder again.
I got a number this time.
555-2804, area code 301.
I need an address.
A name, if you can get it for me.
All right, I'm at, uh... same prefix, 1517.
Thanks, Danny.
- That was fast.
- Terry?
Is that you?
Yeah. Who's this?
They shot me, Terry. Oh, God...
I've been in the water for three days.
I'm hurt.
- Where are you now?
- I'm at a payphone.
I'm gonna pick you up. Where are you?
Terry...
Hello?
You OK?
Are you there?
Hello?
Hello? This man's been hurt.
I think he needs medical attention.
What's the street?
- I'm gonna call an ambulance.
- Sir?
Don't hang up.
- I got it.
- Hi, Danny. Let me get...
...the address.
- You ready?
Mulder?
I'm just writing it down.
The number belongs to a company
called Zeus Storage.
- 1616, Pandora Street.
- Yeah. 1616, Pandora Street.
- That's it.
- Right. Thanks.
OK, we've got a white male. Weak vitals
with severe dyspnoea and hypotension.
He also has a green fluid coming from
a wound in his right upper quadrant.
I don't know what that is.
Any response to ventilation?
No. And we're noticing
a hyposonant-sounding chest.
- He's going real blue.
- OK. You've got a tension pneumothorax.
Perform a thoracotomy
to release the pressure in his chest.
OK. I need a cannula.
We're gonna do a needle decompression.
Ow!
- Mobile men, what's going on?
- Agh!
Mobile men, can you hear me?
Mobile men, answer me!
Mobile men, what is the problem?
Mobile men, come in, please!
- Mulder.
- It's me.
- He's alive, Scully.
- Who?
The fugitive. The driver of the silver Ciera.
He called the doctor's house.
- Where is he now?
- I don't know. Where are you?
I'm at the Georgetown Microbiology
Department. I've got something for you.
Is it smaller than a silver Ciera?
Much.
And it's not silver, it's green.
What is it?
Some kind of bacteria.
Each containing virus.
And it looks as if
Berube may have been cloning them.
They also contain
something like chloroplasts.
Plant cells. But they've
never seen anything like it here.
Any idea what he was doing with them?
The only reason you'd clone a virus
instead of bacteria...
...is in order to inject it
into something living.
It's called gene therapy
and it's still highly experimental.
Maybe that's what he was doing
with the monkeys.
Can they tell you anything else there?
Yeah. They're just about to run some
primary cell cultures and a DNA sequence.
Now, I may be understating
the strangeness of this, Mulder.
Bacteria like this...
It may have existed,
but not for millions of years.
Not since before our ancestors
first crawled out of the sea.
Are you there, Mulder?
- Mulder?
- Yeah.
Scully, keep up the good work.
- Agent Scully.
- Oh, Dr Carpenter. I fell asleep.
I've done some work.
These are the DNA sequences
from the bacteria sample you brought in.
You know a little about molecular biology.
Do you know what you're looking at?
- Yeah. I think those are genes.
- Right.
They're called base pairs. Each pair
is made up of something called a nucleotide.
Only four nucleotides exist in DNA.
Four.
And through some miracle of design
that we have yet to fathom...
...every living thing is created
out of these four basic building blocks.
What you're looking at...
...is a sequence of genes
from the bacteria sample.
Normally, we'd find no gaps
in the sequence.
But with these bacteria we do.
Why is that?
I don't know why.
But I tell you,
under any other circumstances...
...my first call would have been
to the government.
What exactly did you find?
A fifth and sixth DNA nucleotide.
A new base pair.
Agent Scully, what you are looking at...
It exists nowhere in nature.
It would have to be by definition...
...extraterrestrial.
Hello?
Mulder?
Where on earth have you been?
I've been trying to call you all night.
I had a situation. I left my phone in the car.
Mulder...
That bacteria I had analysed...
They're saying
that it doesn't exist in nature.
that it could be extraterrestrial.
- Scully.
- What?
How soon can you be here?
There's something I gotta show you.
Wait a second.
Mulder?
I just want to say that I was wrong.
That's all right. Don't worry about it.
No. Um...
If you'd have listened to me,
we wouldn't be here right now.
I should know by now
to trust your instincts.
Why? Nobody else does.
You know,
I've always held science as sacred.
I've always put my trust
in the accepted facts.
And what I saw last night...
For the first time in my life,
I don't know what to believe.
Well, whatever it is you do believe, Scully...
...when you walk into that room...
...nothing sacred will hold.
There were tanks here...
...and five bodies suspended in solution.
There were computers monitoring them.
They were alive, Scully. Underwater.
- What happened to them?
-  God only knows.
Most likely they've been destroyed.
Ms Scully, we've met ever so briefly.
- Destroyed by whom?
- I don't know.
I don't believe you.
There are limits to my knowledge,
Mr Mulder.
Inside the intelligence community
there are so-called black organisations.
Groups within groups
conducting covert activities...
...unknown at the highest levels...
I was chased by three men last night.
If you were chased, you would have been
killed. Those men are trained for that...
...and they are trained well.
- Were those the men who killed Dr Berube?
- Presumably.
- Why?
- Why?!
Good Lord! You've worked so hard
and you still don't see it!
Dr Berube was conducting human
experiments with extraterrestrial viruses.
Yes! But that's been going on for years.
We've had the tissue since 1947...
...but not the technology.
Roswell?
Roswell was a smoke screen. We've had
a half a dozen better salvage operations.
Dr Berube was killed
because his work was too successful.
You're standing in the room
where the first DNA transplant took...
...the first human-alien hybrid was created.
Six volunteer patients, all terminally ill.
One...
...Dr William Secare, a friend of Dr Berube's,
was dying of melanoma cancer.
And as a result of the ET gene therapy...
...all six patients treated in this room
began to recover from their illnesses.
Dr Secare was able to live
a more or less normal life.
As normal as possible for a man
who has developed inhuman strength...
...and the ability to breathe underwater.
- That's how he was able to elude capture.
- Mm.
What was he running from?
Dr Secare was never
supposed to have survived!
Dr Berube's research
was part of a top-secret
government project at Los Alamos.
All they were interested in
was the technology, the science.
To have a hybrid living out in the real world?
Too great a liability.
I mean, what if he should need
emergency medical procedure?
The man has a blood chemistry
that is alien and very likely toxic.
If that story hit the press...
- It was just easier to kill Dr Secare.
- Of course.
There was only one problem.
Dr Berube was able to warn him.
There's just one thing I don't understand.
Why you gave us so little to go on
in the beginning...
...and why you're giving us so much now.
I didn't anticipate the speed
of their clean-up operation.
They're systematically
destroying all the evidence.
Dr Berube, the bodies here...
Without the evidence,
you two have no case.
Who would believe the story I just told you?
You must put together
everything you have found...
...and you must find Dr Secare
before they do.
I'll have no further contact
with you on this matter.
I'm going to Georgetown
to get all the lab work.
I'm gonna find Dr Secare.
Where?
I don't know. I'm gonna trust my instincts!
Excuse me.
I'm looking for Dr Ann Carpenter.
I can't reach her by phone
and she's not in her office.
She was in a terrible car accident.
Her whole family.
And Dr Carpenter is, um... dead.
Dr Secare?
Wait!
I'll protect you.
Agh!
Your cellular phone's
been ringing off the hook.
I'm a popular guy.
Why don't you answer it for me?
Oh, I don't like talking on the phone.
I have this thing about unsecured lines.
When you feel like talking,
let me know, though.
He's not home.
Where is he? He's been gone all night.
I wish I knew.
Something's happened to him.
- They won't kill him.
- How do you know that?
He's become too high-profile and you've
got evidence that could expose them.
I don't have any! They took the evidence
and may have killed in order to get it.
Listen to me.
- Evidence still exists.
- Where?
It may be difficult to obtain,
but with your medical background...
- ..I might be able to get you inside.
- Inside where?
High containment facility,
Fort Marlene, Maryland.
- What do they have there?
- The wellspring, Ms Scully.
The original tissue.
If they've got Agent Mulder,
they might be willing to make a deal.
It could save his life.
Clear.
Name?
Dana Scully.
- Company or institution?
- Federal government.
Project password?
Purity control.
Log in, please.
You're late.
- Do you have it?
- Yes.
Good. They're willing to make the exchange.
- You spoke to them?
- Yes.
- I'll take the parcel.
- No, sir.
I'll make the exchange.
I made the deal, Scully.
They're expecting me.
- I don't trust you.
- You've got no one else to trust!
I don't know who you are.
I know nothing about you.
Oh, for God's sake! Don't screw this up!
Let me tell you something.
In 1987 a group of children were given what
they thought was a routine inoculation.
What they were injected with...
...was a clone DNA from the contents
of that package you're holding, as a test.
That's the people you're dealing with!
- So why give it back to them?
- To save Mulder's life!
- At the risk of so many other lives?
- It's the tip of the iceberg.
You and Mulder must bring it to light.
Now give me the parcel.
Give me the parcel, Scully!
No!
Mulder! Mulder!
Trust...
Trust... no one.
Hello?
Hey, Scully, it's me.
Where are you?
They're shutting us down, Scully.
What?
They called me in tonight.
They said they're gonna
reassign us to other sections.
Who told you that?
Skinner.
He said word came down
from the top of the Executive Branch.
Mulder...
- It's over, Scully.
- Well, you have to lodge a protest.
- They can't...
- Yes, they can.
What are you gonna do?
I'm...
...not gonna give up. I can't give up.
Not as long as the truth is out there.
Sarah Emery
I made this!