Here. Let me do it.
Put your number in, then your card.
What's your number, Roland?
Three fifteen.
See how easy it is?
- Engine efficiency?
- 94 percent.
We need more!
- How's the back pressure?
- What do you think? Climbing.
Increase the blade inclination.
- I said, increase the blade inclination!
- Inclination is pi over nine!
We've reached maximum velocity.
No!
Let it go. It will work!
The engine'll destroy itself!
I won't do that.
It's not going to destroy itself.
Come on! We're almost there!
- Something's wrong with our equations.
- What happened?
- Nothing. Surnow pulled the plug.
- I'm protecting the baby!
- And four years of work, Frank.
- Work that's going to add up to zilch.
Unless we show some progress,
they're going to pull the plug on us, Ron.
He's right. You should've continued the test.
Someone'll crack Mach 15.
I want it to be us.
Lwon'tjeopardise everything because you
two can't wait to see your name in print!
It's the print that gets the money, Ron.
If you want to go down in flames
together, fine. You go ahead.
I'm going to do the math.
Good night, Dr Keats.
What the hell?!
Roland! Open the door!
Open the door! Roland, I want you
to listen to me very carefully.
We have to open this door,
Roland. Stop typing!
Roland!
Roland! Open the door!
What are you doing?!
Open the door!
Roland, are you listening?!
Aagh! No!
Aaaagh!
Aagh!
- How was the wedding?
- The part where the groom passed out...
- ..or the dog bit the drummer?
- Did you catch the bouquet?
Maybe. Is that what you couldn't
talk to me about over the phone?
The project they say
doesn't exist does exist.
- The Icarus Project?
- The next generation in jet engine design...
...capable of doubling speeds
using half the fuel.
At least in theory.
And Ronald Surnow was
an aeronautical scientist...
...who worked on it here at the university?
- Yes.
- How close are they?
I'm not sure, but Surnow's the second
scientist to die in the last six months.
OK. But how is this an X-File?
You don't think this is
about UFO technology?
There's something unexplainable,
but not unidentifiable.
- Keats?
- There.
Dr Keats?
We're with the FBI.
Agent Mulder. This is Agent Scully.
We understand you discovered Dr Surnow.
What was left of him.
How do you suppose he became
trapped in the wind tunnel?
Someone must have shut him in.
- The door is operated from there.
- By computer?
I've already been through this
with the police.
Another member of your team
died recently. Isn't that correct?
Yes. Arthur Grable.
He was killed in an automobile
accident in November.
I'm Frank Nollette. I'm also on the project.
- Are you certain it was an accident?
- What are you driving at?
Your work seems to be a perfect target
for industrial espionage.
Who wrote this?
Ron was working on it when I left.
The handwriting here doesn't seem
to match any of the other handwriting.
It isn't mine.
What about Roland Fuller?
Uh... Roland's the, uh... janitor.
According to the police report,
he was the only other person here.
- Roland didn't do that.
- How do you know?
Let's just say Roland isn't
exactly a rocket scientist.
Here.
Tracy.
With stars.
Roland?
There are some people here
would like to talk with you.
Uh-oh.
I went off the paper.
- Sorry.
- That's all right, Roland.
Tracy.
Would you like to come
help me in the TV room?
OK.
Hi, Roland. Mind if we sit down?
Thanks.
Do you mind if we ask you
a couple of questions?
- Do you remember working last night?
- Uh-huh.
Do you remember seeing anything unusual?
Seeing any strangers?
Did, um...
Did Dr Surnow or Dr Keats...
...or Dr Nollette do anything unusual?
Nope.
You must like stars.
One hundred and forty-seven.
- Sorry?
- Smm.
You like numbers too, huh?
Roland, let me help you.
One... two...
...three...
...four... five...
...six...
- ..seven...
- Roland, is everything OK?
Roland, are you all right?
Eleven...
- Twelve... thirteen...
- What happened?
What did you say to upset him so?!
Sixteen...
Seventeen...
It's definitely the work of a fourth individual.
The doctors' cursive standards don't
match what you found on the white board.
Will you do me a favour and try this?
- What is it?
- Something Roland was doodling.
- You don't really think Roland...
- He was the only other person in the lab.
But we're talking about a sophisticated
fluid dynamics equation.
Roland barely has an IQ of 70.
You saw his facility with math.
Don't some autistic individuals
display unusual abilities?
Yes, but even savants behave
only as human calculators.
They can perform certain functions...
...but they can't tell you the value
of anything or the meaning.
I hate to take sides,
but the bottom line is no.
The terminal stroke on the six,
the roof on the five...
I'm sorry. He didn't write it.
Aagh!
An organic object exposed to liquid nitrogen
at minus 320 degrees will freeze...
...exhibiting great tensile strength...
...but is vulnerable to stress
from compression or impact.
I've seen this demonstrated on a fish before.
I don't think they'll do this
on Beakman's World.
Has this been dusted?
- Treat yourself.
- Thanks.
Hey, Scully! Look at these files.
KMAN must be Keats.
This file was turned off at 12.31 last night.
But look. Someone else entered a file
under the name ARTHUR after 12.31.
And worked on it for nearly five hours.
Well, it couldn't have been Keats.
Judging from the rigor of the body,
he was dead around 12.30.
So someone came in, killed Keats...
...and then just did some work
on an old Dr Grable file?
I can't access the ARTHUR file.
We'll need the password.
Try... 15626.
How did you know that that...?
This is Arthur Grable's work on the same
equations the others were working on.
Look at all those entries.
Someone has been continuing
his work since he died.
How did you know what the password was?
Wave goodbye! Wave goodbye!
Wave goodbye! Bye-bye!
Wave goodbye!
Roland?
Why did you sleep in your clothes?
Well, let's get you dressed.
You have visitors.
I'm not supposed to talk to them.
Who told you that?
Remember that talk we had...
...about being shy?
These are nice people, Roland.
Hey, Roland, you've got more shirts
than I do.
This one would look stylin' today.
What do you think?
- The green one.
- The green one?
Please.
Mrs Stodie, can I talk to you a second?
See you later, Roland.
This one?
There you go.
- Do you like your job at the college, Roland?
- Yes.
I hear you're very good at it.
Do you remember how you got your job?
A man talked to Mrs Stodie.
What man?
Dr Grable.
Was Dr Grable nice to you?
Yes.
When did you last speak to him?
Last week? The day before?
Dr Grable died.
I'm sorry.
People die.
They go away.
And they're not supposed to come back.
Has Roland ever mentioned
the name Arthur?
That was Dr Grable's first name,
but we only called him Dr Grable.
I doubt Roland even knew
his first name was Arthur.
Mrs Stodie, can I get a copy
of Roland's file and past history?
- Our patients' histories are confidential.
- I understand, but I can obtain them.
The less time we spend in court,
the more time we have to help Roland.
Roland Fuller was hired by Arthur Grable.
He specifically wanted
a mentally challenged person.
Are you suggesting Arthur Grable
hired Roland in order to use him?
Are you suggesting
Arthur Grable is not dead?
If he had intentions of killing
Nollette, Keats and Surnow...
...why not set it up to appear
the least likely suspect?
But, by the look of this, he's hamburger.
Maybe he staged it.
That would explain why his work is
continuing on, six months after his... death.
This obituary says Arthur Grable was born
in Seattle. His father was a big banker.
His mother was active
in a number of charities.
Only child. Summa cum laude in physics.
Doctoral and postdoctoral in
aeronautical engineering at Harvey Mudd.
Brilliant future tragically cut short.
Roland's also from Seattle.
He spent most of his life
at the Heritage Halfway House.
The identity of his parents
has been sealed.
There's very little information before
the age of three, when he went to the home.
Does it say when he was born?
July 15, 1952.
That's also Arthur's birth date.
Don't you wish you could fly?
I can.
When I dream.
People can do anything
in a dream, you know.
Once...
One time I had a dream we were married...
...and lived in a house.
Do you have dreams, Roland?
You can tell me.
Roland?
Who's Arthur?
Aagh!
I'm sorry, Roland!
I'm sorry!
Roland!
Go away!
I don't want to hurt you!
Go away.
- Is that you?
- Yes.
Cool do!
What's the story here?
Um...
A quantum physics professor of mine
at Harvey Mudd, uh... flunked me.
He challenged a tenet of one of my theories.
A theory I later published in Nature.
Anyway, uh... to get back at him...
One afternoon
we decided to take his car apart...
...and put it back together again
in his office, and left it running.
- Mmm. An egghead classic.
- It was Arthur Grable's idea.
- Is that Arthur Grable sitting on the chair?
- Yeah.
- Was he a practical joker?
- Atop of all his brilliance...
...he had a genius for elaborate schemes.
Could he be making it seem like a man
with a 70 IQ is gaining access to...
...and, uh... operating his old computer files?
Arthur would still have to be alive.
- Could he have faked his own death?
- No.
The police report on the auto accident
was woefully incomplete.
A dry road surface.
No mechanical problems.
The body was never admitted to
a county morgue and there was no funeral.
If you are trying...
...to suggest that Arthur Grable killed
Surnow and Keats, and is after me next...
...you're way off.
Art could not have done the murders.
How can you be so certain?
This is Arthur Grable.
Because of massive damage to
his body caused by the accident...
...we could only preserve the head.
Wouldn't your client find it inconvenient...
...to be thawed out in the future, only
to discover he had no functional mobility?
By the time science figures
a way to revive our clients...
- You'll also know how to clone new bodies.
- Exactly!
This technology is progressing faster than
anyone thought possible. Ask anyone here.
While for us the passing of each second
brings our bodies closer to death...
...for our clients it brings them closer to life.
These fluctuations - do they happen often?
We've had some problems
with Dr Grable's capsule.
Our technicians checked it
and found nothing.
Is it possible the brain is causing it?
No.
But we are looking for the explanation.
The patient remains preserved as long as
there's liquid nitrogen in the capsule.
May we take a look at
Arthur Grable's records?
Thank you.
Dr Barrington,
as to future medical science...
...what requirements will exist
to be an organ donor?
Same as today - compatible genetic
make-up. It's best if the donor's related.
Mulder.
Arthur Grable put down only one donor.
Roland Fuller and Arthur Grable
have the same birthday.
I think they're twins.
Older or younger?
Same age. Just less hairy
and with better eyesight.
- Gotcha. And the moustache?
- No, lose the whole beard.
Next?
Close-cropped hair,
with a slightly receding widow's peak.
Lose the glasses.
- That's Roland.
- Give or take a few pounds.
Tell me about your dreams, Roland.
It's all right. I won't tell anybody.
You know, I had a dream last night.
I dreamt I was swimming in this pool.
And I could see my father undenNater.
But when I dove down,
the water stung my eyes.
And there was another man at the pool...
...watching me.
He upset me.
He was asking me questions
I didn't want to answer.
I had to leave.
I couldn't find my father.
I can't tell you my dreams.
Why not?
Bad.
Your dreams are bad, Roland.
Not you.
You're a good person.
I hit Tracy.
Your dreams make you hit Tracy?
You know how to work this toy, Roland?
Here.
You see, the way you work that toy...
...is like what's happening to you.
You're the spaceship, Roland.
And your dreams are the controls.
Who...
Who runs the controls?
Have you seen this man recently?
Come on, Arthur. We have to
say bye-bye to Roland.
Bye.
Roland...
Roland!
Roland, stop!
We need to keep Roland under observation.
Roland!
- He's trying to get away.
- Roland!
Roland!
Nollette's gone. We should arrange
a security guard to find him.
No one's gonna provide anything...
...once you explain how Roland Fuller
is capable of these murders.
You've got a brother, don't you, Scully?
Yeah. I've got an older one
and a younger one.
Have you ever thought about calling one
of them, and then suddenly they call you?
Is this a way for me to lower
my long-distance charges?
I believe in psychic connections.
Evidence suggests it's stronger between
family members. Especially twin siblings.
OK... Maybe. But in this case, one sibling
has closer ties to a frozen fudgsicle...
...than he does to his own brother.
Arthur Grable is not dead. He's in a state of
consciousness no human has returned from.
What if that state allows one
to develop psychic ability...
...that the conscious mind is too
preoccupied to explore or believe in?
He could use that to control
his brother to kill the scientists.
But why? He's been working
with them for years.
OK. Let's go.
I have to call my brother.
We've got to find Nollette.
Let's talk to campus security.
- We go this way?
- No, we go left.
Well...
...wherever you are, Arthur...
...I'm sure you'll appreciate this.
Arthur and Roland Grable...
...born at Puget Presbyterian to
Mr and Mrs Lewis Grable on July 15, 1952.
Arthur was four minutes older than Roland.
Identical twins.
Which means that they're the result of
a single egg fertilised by a single sperm.
Studies suggest that in some cases...
...the identical twin arises early
in the embryonic stage.
A mutation in one cell is rejected
by other cells as foreign.
Roland's condition is the result
of a damaged chromosome
rejected by Arthur's cells?
In a way that would explain Arthur's genius
and Roland's mathematical gift.
In a way.
Agent Scully.
This is Larry Barrington
at the Avalon Foundation.
- We've got a situation here.
- Uh-huh.
Last night we had a break-in at the facility.
That's right.
It's Arthur Grable's storage unit.
His thermostat's been compromised.
- Was there any tissue damage?
- We're trying to assess that now.
The temperature's still rising. Something's
blocking our access to the cooling program.
Someone tampered with
Arthur Grable's capsule.
They're attempting to stabilise it.
Nollette?
What...
What is this?
If I have seen further than other men...
...it's because I have stood
on the shoulders of giants.
No...
This isn't yours.
It's amazing.
There's this body, sitting there
in front of me, talking.
But you're controlling it, Arthur.
You...
...took my work!
What good was
your work going to do you?
You died before you could finish it,
before you could publish it.
It was mine!
When I saw the writing on the board,
I knew someone had found the key.
Mach 15 was within our reach.
Our futures were guaranteed.
Ironic, isn't it?
You did all the work, and I get all the glory.
No!
Yes.
Yes, Arthur.
I was here,
working on the intake problem...
...moments away from a solution,
when you attacked me.
Fortunately, I was carrying a gun.
After the murder of my colleagues,
who could blame me?
That's... That's interesting.
I've got it!
That's it!
Arthur!
Arthur! Open the door!
Arthur...
...how do you stop this? Tell me how!
- Arthur!
- Hey!
Roland, we need you to help us.
Please, we need you
to help us to stop the machine.
Try to remember how.
Roland, you've got to help him
or he's going to die.
Wave goodbye, Arthur!
- Come on, Roland.
- I can't remember!
Aagh!
He'll be held in psychiatric
custody for evaluation.
Is he being charged with a crime?
The DA hasn't made that determination yet.
We've recommended he be remanded to
your custody as soon as the court allows it.
How could this happen?
Roland never exhibited
any violent tendencies.
It's my belief that he wasn't
acting under his own volition.
What do you mean?
This is the work of Arthur, Roland's brother.
It's a new theory of
jet propulsion, unfinished.
In the last two weeks, Roland
has completed the calculations.
How?
We're not sure. All we know
is that Roland was somehow...
...able to finish his brother's research.
Roland?
Where are you going?
Roland, don't go.
I have to.
OK. Bye.
Tracy...
Wait.
Keep my stars.
I love you.
Me, too.
Sally Lewis
I made this!