Relax, they'll be here.
The bank's gonna close in five minutes.
- Sure it wasn't a bogus tip?
- No, it's real.
I've been on this long enough.
I know the difference.
Besides, I can feel it.
I can feel them. I'm inside their heads.
Just as long as you keep yours!
Message received, Agent Scully.
Loud and clear.
Position Five, this is Agent Willis.
Do you copy?
- What, are you nervous?
- Nope.
I just don't want our luck to run out.
Baby, you are my luck.
And no matter what happens...
...whenever I look up at the stars...
...I know you're gonna be
looking up at the same ones.
The same ones, baby.
You make every day like New Year's Eve!
Come on, people! Get down on the floor,
now! Get down on the floor!
I ain't messin' around here! You! Down
on the floor, now! Now, or you're dead!
Everyone! Down on the floor!
Or I'll execute every one of you! Move!
Move! Put the money in the bag. Now!
Now! Move it!
- Faster!
- Dupre!
Drop the gun! FBI! Drop the gun!
Now!
Clear!
Watch him carefully.
11 minutes, 55 seconds.
Clear!
Come on, Jack.
He's been flatlined for 12 minutes.
Another amp of epi,
and we'll go again at 360.
Clear!
Still no pulse.
We've done all we can. I'm sorry.
All right, let's call off.
- You want me to pronounce?
- No! You can't give up on him.
- It's been over 13 minutes. He's dead.
- Go up to 400.
We lost him. Let him go.
I'm a doctor! Go up to 400,
or I'll do it myself!
Clear!
Still no pulse.
Give him another amp of epi intracardial
and go up to 400 again.
Do it!
Clear!
Again!
- Come on, Jack.
- Clear!
Come on!
We got a rhythm.
Don't ask me how, but he's back!
BP's 80 over 50 and climbing. 90 over 50.
Hello, Mr Goldbaum.
How are we doing tonight?
I'm just going to adjust your drip.
I'll check on you again later.
Any word from Willis?
Still missing. He hasn't
been home or to the office.
I heard something about a mutilation...
Yeah. Three fingers on Dupre's left hand
were severed by surgical shears.
We lifted prints. They're Willie's.
He said he was chasing this guy
for almost a year?
He lived the case.
It was all he ever thought about.
What are you thinking?
That maybe this is some kind
of post-trauma psychosis.
Like the way soldiers sometimes
mutilate the body of a dead enemy.
That still doesn't explain
why he would just vanish.
Dupre's partner... Who was she?
Lula Phillips.
They met while she was serving a 10-year
sentence for manslaughter in Maryland.
- He was a prison guard.
- Until the warden found out their secret.
According to Lula's cell mate,
they carried on quite a torrid romance.
It says here she was released
on May 2nd, 1993.
One week before the first robbery
at Annapolis Savings and Loan.
A 65-year-old female teller
was pistol-whipped.
Died from a massive subdural haemorrhage.
She didn't put the money
in the bag fast enough!
- Lovely couple!
- Well, apparently they took turns.
One pulling a job,
while the other one drove getaway.
Between the two of them
they've killed seven people
and got away with close to $100,000.
That's a lot of money, now that
she doesn't have to split it.
Well, we're putting her face out there.
Local newspapers,
America's Most Wanted...
Am I boring you?
- They were married.
- Yeah, last May in Atlantic City. So what?
So I don't think this was a
simple necrophiliac mutilation.
Willis sliced and diced those fingers
to get at the wedding ring.
Anybody here?
Lula?
Baby, baby, baby...
Damn!
It's a left thumb print.
Look at these two bifurcations here.
Whoever was holding that cleaver
used his left hand.
- "Whoever"? It was Willis.
- Willis is right-handed.
I checked his pistol grip at the armoury.
But the bank surveillance tapes
show Dupre is left-handed.
I'm not sure where you're going with this.
How long did Willis flatline
before you revived him?
Just over 13 minutes.
This EKG strip recorded
his cardiac activity at the time.
In your medical opinion,
what does that look like?
It could be anything.
Instrument malfunction,
electrical overload...
But what does it look like?
Two heartbeats.
Dupre and Willis went into cardiac arrest
at the exact same time, right?
Right...
For a period of minutes,
both men were technically dead.
- Technically. But we resuscitated Willis.
- You resuscitated his body.
Mulder...
Two men died in that crash room, Scully.
One man came back. The question is...
...which one?
What can you tell me about
near-death experiences, Agent Scully?
The usual stuff. The tunnel, the light, people
rising up and viewing their own bodies.
As a scientist,
how do you account for the phenomenon?
Some sort of dissociative
hallucinatory activity.
Hm.
Half of all the adults who have had a
near-death experience cannot wear a watch.
The increased electrical activity in their
bodies renders the watches inoperable.
I know this sounds kooky,
but, as any biologist will tell you...
...when cells die and genetic material
begins to unfold...
...a tremendous charge of energy is released.
Doctor Varnes believes this is responsible...
...for the transformational nature
of the experience.
People do return from the
event profoundly changed.
Changed how?
Personality shifts, perceived
psychic abilities, increased zest for life.
What about the negative consequences?
They're rare. But in the process of dying...
...there is a time
during which the body is vulnerable.
- I don't understand.
- Well...
...there was a pilot in my support group
who died in a commuter plane crash...
...along with his three passengers.
This was a few years ago.
Now, he recalls floating up...
...in a brilliant aura of light, and then feeling
an overwhelming need to return to his body.
He was revived in the ambulance on the way
to the hospital. The only survivor.
Soon after that, the visions started.
Visions of making love to his wife,
in ways that weren't in his memory.
Turns out that one of
the dead passengers on the plane
was having an affair with his wife.
The dead passenger's memory, his...
...his consciousness,
had survived through the pilot.
- What happened?
- The pilot became increasingly disoriented.
Schizophrenic, his doctor claims.
He strangled his wife
with an extension cord.
That's a nice story!
I don't discount the near-death experience.
It can be explained empirically...
- ..by stimulation of the temporal lobe.
- I sense a big "but" coming!
I still believe that Jack's disappearance
can be explained in psychological terms.
For instance?
The stress of the case, the trauma
of being shot, Jack's personality...
- How well do you know him?
- We dated. For almost a year.
He was my instructor at the Academy.
The plot thickens!
We even had the same birthday.
We used to celebrate in some dive
in Stafford that had a slanted pool table.
But it was always so hard for Jack to...
...relax. It was impossible for him, really.
He was always so... intense,
so relentlessly determined.
Do you believe he's predisposed
to this type of psychotic episode?
It's a long way from saying Jack
had a near-death experience...
...to saying his body's been
inhabited by Warren Dupre.
A long way!
What the hell...?!
- You're such a creature of habit, Tommy.
- Who the hell are you?
- Get outta bed.
- I ain't got no clothes on.
Get outta bed!
I don't wanna shoot you lying down.
Who are you - the rent man? Cos I'm
all paid up. I swear. I'm not kiddin'.
- Come on, you can go ask Cosmo.
- Shut up!
- Where is she?
- Where's who?
- Your sister.
- Huh! Lula?
Look, I don't know. I don't know, I swear!
I was just waiting to see her on the news.
What'd I tell you?
Check it out.
The sound's busted.
Looks like they're gonna find her
before you do, pal!
Is that what you think?
It's not what I think.
I miss her, Tommy.
I miss her so bad!
That's why I came back.
- Do I know you from somewhere?
- Everything I see...
...I see her.
Jesus, man! You're bleeding.
Even ugliness is beautiful... because of her.
- OK, what are you doing?
- You set us up, Tommy.
You sold us out to the FBI!
Dupre?
Neighbours heard a gunshot,
but nobody checked it out.
Patrol guys responded this morning
to an anonymous 911 and found him here.
Except the rats found him first.
The victim's name was Thomas Phillips.
That's Lula's brother.
There's not a lot of family resemblance left,
between the rats and the.45 in the face!
-  Oh, I hate this nicotine stuff.
-  What's the story?
Oh, he's single. He's lived here
alone for the past seven months.
A few priors - small stuff, mostly.
B and E, narcotics possession.
Nothing like his big sister.
- Was the TV on when they found him?
- No. Why?
I don't think Tommy was much of a reader,
since he doesn't have any books.
From the position of the body,
I'd say maybe he was watching
the tube when he was shot.
- Print kit's over there. Knock yourself out!
-  Get out of my way, Ace!
Regulations state, to gain access
to a crime scene, you gotta show ID!
Looks like you were right.
Excuse me.
Jack...
Is there a problem here?
No, I just, uh... I don't have any ID.
Would you tell this gentleman who I am?
Officer, this is Agent Jack Willis.
Violent Crimes Section
of the Washington Bureau.
Come on, let's talk out here.
I was just doing my job, miss!
Willis, what happened?! Half the Bureau's
been looking for you. Where have you been?
I don't know. I just... wasn't myself.
I just kinda... woke up out on the street!
- I'm taking you back to the hospital.
- No way! I'm staying right here!
- You're not ready to be here.
- Who says?!
Jack, you're recovering
from a major trauma.
It's a miracle you're even able to walk!
- This is Tommy Phillips' place, right?
- Jack...
Was he killed with a.45?
As a matter of fact, he was.
He was! That's Lula's weapon of choice.
I know these people. I've been after them
for a long time. We're halfway there!
- You did open the book on this one.
- And I'll be there when it's closed!
All right.
But, as a colleague and as a friend...
...I recommend you have a full medical
evaluation. Physical and psychological.
All right, fair enough.
Jack! Good to see you back
among the living.
- It's good to be back.
- Jack.
- So what have we got here?
- Mulder here found a print on the TV.
A partial oblique. And it's not the victim's.
Good work, Agent Mulder. I'm impressed!
That's fancy shooting.
I gotta get re-certified before
they give me my weapon back.
Well, by the looks of it, I wouldn't
worry about re-certification.
- Is there anything else you wanted?
- Yeah, it's Scully's birthday.
I was wondering if you'd sign that for me.
Sure! Be glad to.
Always glad to celebrate the good times.
There you go!
Happy birthday, Scully.
You're two months early.
It's from Willis. I thought you two
had the same birthday?
- We do.
- Well, that's news to him.
I asked him to sign it.
And he signed it with his left hand.
You tested him.
Yeah. I found out evidence from
the Phillips murder is missing.
- What evidence?
- The print we lifted. Our best lead is gone.
Someone stole it before the lab
had a chance to take a look at it.
- And you think Willis is responsible?
- I'm not sure Willis is Willis.
Can you at least accept the possibility...
...that, during his near-death experience,
psychic transference occurred?
Can't you accept the possibility
that this isn't an X-File?!
Aside from the expected level
of post-trauma stress...
...Jack passed both of his evaluations -
physical and psychological.
Just because someone forgets a birthday,
it doesn't mean that he's been possessed!
When I was studying for my medical boards,
I forgot my birthday, too!
Did you forget how to sign your name?
This is a copy of the automobile requisition
form Willis filed the day before he was shot.
Compare the signatures.
Like I said, Mulder - stress. All right?
It can significantly affect
someone's cursive standard.
I'm afraid this doesn't prove a thing.
Agent Willis here.
Jack?
- Where are you going?
- We got a break!
- A landlord thinks he's got our girl.
- Hotline?
Yeah. Saw her picture in the post office.
There's the address.
- Jack, can I ask you something?
- Yeah, sure.
The Phillips murder. The print
Mulder lifted off the TV. It's missing.
And?
And you were carrying the evidence back.
Are you implying something, Agent Scully?
I don't know anything about any missing
print. Now, I'm ten minutes away...
...from closing the biggest case
of my career. Are you coming?
What's the apartment number
again?
202.
Oh, yeah.
- What was this guy's name?
- Multrevich.
- Multrevich?
All right, all right, all right!
Mr Multrevich, I'm from the FBI. Jack Willis.
- We spoke on the phone, right?
- Oh, yeah.
Have you ever seen this lady?
Yeah. 207. Two days ago.
First and last month - cash.
- Where's 207?
- Down the hallway.
We want you to go back
inside your apartment...
...and stay away from the windows. Thanks.
Where's our backup?
You said you called them, right?
Should've been here ten minutes ago.
She may be running down a fire escape!
I'm gonna call in again.
Look! That's her!
- Where is she? Where'd she go?!
- I'll check back here.
Yeeargghhh!
Face down! Face down!
Hands behind your back!
- Now!
She's all yours, Jack.
Yeah... Like a dog on a leash.
I already cuffed her.
They're for you, Scully. Put 'em on.
- What's going on, Jack?
- Put 'em on. Or I'll blow you in half.
Jack...
Shut up! Put 'em on!
Come on, baby.
Come on, get up, baby.
Look at you...
Your face is all dirty.
- Keep your stinking hands off me!
- Baby!
You ain't gonna believe where I've been.
Sure it's crazy. You don't think
I know it's crazy? This isn't my face!
These aren't my hands!
But it's me in here! And I know you.
I know everything about you, baby.
Come on, ask me something.
Your birthday is April 7th.
Your favourite colour is red.
Come on...
Come on, ask me something else.
Come on, ask me!
OK... OK, what did we do
after we got married?
Right after?
- After that.
- Well... we went down to the beach.
I took out my buck knife
and I sliced open my palm.
And then I slit open your palm.
And we let the blood drip
down in the water.
- Then what did you say to me?
- I said...
..."This is so we can be married
in all the oceans of the world."
And then I made you a solemn oath.
To never take this ring off my finger.
Ever!
And I mean to keep that promise.
This is... This is just too weird!
I can't believe it's really you!
Don't worry, baby.
It won't make any difference in the dark.
-  We'll be in touch.
- When do I get my reward?
We'll call you.
Now I'm worried. 12 hours with no word?
I don't get it. Why's her car still sitting out
front? Why didn't Willis call for backup?
Because it wasn't Willis
who answered the hotline.
- You heard the recording. It was his voice.
- Forget it, Bruskin.
Plus which... the manager
just ID'd him and Scully.
I said, forget it, Bruskin!
This isn't one of your X-File theories, is it?
It doesn't matter what I think.
We're still after the same thing.
- Mulder.
- FBI centrex operator. Please hold.
- Yeah.
- Guess who, Ace.
Willis?!
That depends on who you ask, don't it?
Where's Scully?
You're the FBI!
You figure it out!
Let me talk to her.
Yeah, sure.
- Mulder...
- Dana, are you OK?
- Don't...
- Dana?
OK!
That's it! Goodbye!
It's not gonna work, Jack.
You don't think so?
Bureau policy prohibits
negotiating with kidnappers.
But you already know that, don't you, Jack?
Stop calling me that!
Your name is Jack Willis.
You were born February 23, 1957.
- You live at 51 Stanhope...
- My name is Warren James Dupre!
And I was born in Clammouth Falls,
Oregon, in the Year of the Rat!
We spent a weekend up at Pine Barrens.
You taught me how to fish through the ice.
It was your parents' cabin.
Jack, try to remember.
We drove up in a snowstorm.
Come on, Jack!
Don't think I didn't see what you did!
I was like a little slip of paper,
up there on that hospital ceiling.
- I saw everything.
- What did you see?
You left me to die on that table,
while you tried to save your friend!
- You are my friend!
- Too bad he was gone already.
I watched him go. Just saw him slip away
down that long, black tunnel.
No. We brought you back.
You shot me dead!
And then you let me die.
No. You won't kill me, Jack.
You call me that one more time...
...and I'll make you stone cold.
Easy, baby. Easy! Not yet.
Remember, she's our ticket.
Hey!
- Got any more of this soda?
- You just drank the last of it.
Soda...?
How much of that have you had?
- What's it to you?
- Jack Willis is diabetic.
Which means that you are. Too much sugar
in the system could lead to hyperglycaemia.
Maybe that's why
your stomach's hurting so bad.
Abdominal pain is the first sign
of impending diabetic coma.
You need insulin.
I feel myself getting into their heads,
and I'm scared by what I'm feeling.
The intoxicating freedom that comes from
disconnecting action and consequence.
Theirs is a world where nothing
matters but their own needs...
..their own impossible appetites.
And while the pleasure they derive
from acts of violence is clearly sexual...
..it also speaks to what
Warden Jackson called
their "operatic devotion to each other".
It's a love affair... I almost envy.
Cadenceville PD just reported
a drugstore was broken into here...
...on the corner of
Old Forge Road and Madison.
I'm betting that Scully is somewhere
within this five-mile radius.
- Am I missing something?!
- 200 units of NPH insulin were taken.
Willis is diabetic.
Get me a census report. Let's see
how many households we're talking about.
Quick, quick, quick!
My legs are starting to go numb!
Hold on...
- What the hell...?
- Drop the needle.
- Without this medicine, he dies.
- Yeah! So you said.
Now... put it down.
Unless you want me
to put you down with it.
What the hell are you doing?
I need that medicine!
- You still haven't figured it out, have you?
- Figured what out?
It wasn't my brother who set you up!
You?!
Yeah... Me.
How do you think I got away so clean?
The minute you stepped into that bank,
I was out of there.
I got the money and I got rid of you!
At least, I thought I did.
Agh...
Tactical room. This is it!
Mulder.
- Listen carefully.
- Where's Willis?
- Oh, he's here somewhere.
- Let me talk to Scully.
Not this time.
We don't deal unless we know Scully's alive.
She's alive.
She's not happy, but... she's alive.
You listen to me. You lay one hand
on Scully, and so help me God...
If I were you, I'd stop talking
and start passing around the collection hat.
Cos if you ever wanna see Scully again,
it's gonna cost you a million dollars.
Have it by this time tomorrow.
I'll tell you when and where.
We got it. It's a 202 number.
-  Great!
-  It's coming through.
- Here it is.
- Get the address.
- Forget it.
- Why?
It's Scully's cellular number.
They're using her phone.
We can't trace them.
She's not happy, but... she's alive.
If I were you, I'd stop talking
and start passing around the collection hat.
- That last part?
- Yeah. Squelch the voice even more.
Yeah.
Done.
If I were you, I'd stop talking
and start passing around the collection hat.
Yep. Yep! There's something there.
Definitely something at the high end.
Let me throw on an extra Z-14 filter...
and isolate everything over half a decibel.
If I were you, I'd stop talking
and start passing around the collection hat.
There. That engine sound.
Let's clean it up some more!
- If I were you, I'd stop talking and...
Is that a small plane?
Taking off, by the sound of it.
Give me a minute to guess
the altitude within 200ft!
Great!
All right, people! Settle down, grab a seat.
Mulder says he's got something.
What? An alien virus, or new information
on the Kennedy assassination?
Hey, Mulder's all right.
Pay attention,
you might learn something from the man.
From our last phone contact, we've
identified what sounds like light aircraft.
Now, Washington County Regional Airport
happens to fall within our area.
Since takeoffs are north to south...
...it's a fair bet that our target area
lies along this flight path.
For those who remember math, that gives
us an area of three square miles to cover.
Roughly 1,000 households.
With 100 law enforcement officials...
...at about 30 households per man per hour,
we can canvass the entire area
in three hours.
Bruskin will grid the target area
and divide it among the teams.
For those of you... who don't know
already, this one's important to me.
So, um... let's do it right. Thanks.
Let me see Steinberg, Calder, Westin,
Stipley and Mackowitz...
-  Scully?
- Huh?
Was there snow?
Yes... Jack.
There was lots of snow.
- I can't...
- It was December.
It was the weekend after Thanksgiving.
I remember...
...a red stove.
Yeah... That's right.
There was a... There was a wood-burning
stove right in the middle of the room.
Cold, hm?
- Yeah.
- So cold...
I remember... I had to wrap you
in a blanket...
...when the wood ran out.
Yeah.
No... Jack! Don't close your eyes.
Come on, keep talking.
Jack, keep talking! Come on!
Down on the floor, now!
Now, or you're dead!
- I'm gonna execute every one of you!
- No!
No!
Shut up and do it!
Just a second! Who is it?
It's Brother Tate. Could I speak with
you forjust one moment, please?
What do you want?
Just a few minutes of your time, ma'am.
Beautiful day, isn't it?
I wonder if I can interest you
in the word of the Lord?
Leather-bound, in black or red. Your choice.
Go away!
This is 1-4. Target sighted.
Well... I guess it's time to make that call.
He's dead.
It's all on you now.
He's dead because of you.
Well...
Guess it's over.
Whoever you are.
- Agh!
- Don't move!
- Jack!
- Shut up!
I love you.
Don't you know?
You're why I came back.
This is Westin.
They've battened down the hatches.
No clear shot from this side.
What about you guys?
Ditto. Hold your positions
and keep radios at two.
- How do we look?
- Backup's in.
- But we still don't know what's going on.
- We will soon enough.
I kept a bottle of medicine
in the other room. I'll go get it.
What do you say, huh?
I'll get it for you.
Look! Look! Look!
Look, I love you.
- I love you, baby.
- No...
Listen! Listen, we... we still have her.
We can get away with this.
I don't think so, baby. Not this time.
Jack, put the gun down!
You remember that... that
light that I talked about?
-  No...
- It's beautiful.
- There's nothing to be afraid of.
- No!
- FBI!
Freeze!
Jack!
FBI!
Scully. Are you OK?
Jack?!
Hi. I got this from the morgue, along
with the rest of his personal effects.
- I thought you might want it.
- Mm.
"Happy 35th. Love D."
I got it for him three years ago.
Next of kin?
Uh... no.
Jack was an only child.
His parents died when he was in college.
There's a... kid over in Parklawn.
Jack's been his big brother,
so I'm going to go and see him tomorrow.
- What am I gonna tell him?
- The official story.
Which is?
Fugitive Lula Phillips died in
a shoot-out with federal agents.
It also resulted in the death of Special Agent
Jack Willis - killed in the line of duty.
What am I supposed to tell myself?
Good night.
It's not working. It stopped.
At 6.47.
The exact time that Jack
went into cardiac arrest at the hospital.
What does that mean?
It means...
It means whatever you want it to mean.
Good night.
I made this!