Yes.
- Love you.
- And I love you.
- Hello.
- Morning, sir.
Good morning.
- Good morning, Cecil.
-  Top o' the morning to yeh.
Oh, thank you.
- Goodbye, darling!
- Goodbye, Charles!
- What time can I expect you?
- Before supper.
Oh! I forgot what it was like
to spend a day in court.
That's one of the luxuries to hunting
down aliens and genetic mutants.
You rarely get to press charges.
- It's open.
- What?
- It's unlocked.
- That's weird.
- I'm sure I locked it.
- Must be an X-File.
What's that?
I told you I locked the door.
What do you think it is?
Ten to one you can't dance to it.
Greetings, Agent Mulder.
Six months ago, British MP
Reggie Ellicott received a cassette...
..like the one you're listening to now.
Unfortunately, when he popped
the tape into the stereo...
..he armed a device which,
when he tried to exit the car...
..created an explosion
heard five miles away.
The Scotland Yard forensic team could only
identify the poor bastard by dental records.
If only he hadn't reached for the handle
and triggered the detonator!
But how was he to know he was
sitting on enough plastic explosive...
..to lift the car 40 feet...
..and deposit the engine block
on top of a three-storey building?
Aren't we looking rather ghostly?
It's an old friend.
- Aren't you going to thank me?
- For what?
Saving your life. One tends not
to make the same mistake twice.
- I'll try to remember that.
- You left your sense of humour...
- ..in Oxford ten years ago?
- It's one of the few things...
...you didn't drive a stake through.
You know, some mistakes
are worth making twice.
Dana Scully, this is Phoebe Green,
terror of Scotland Yard.
- Hello.
She hates me.
What brings you to the colonies?
Some clever bloke has been giving
the aristocracy a good scare.
Killed off a ranking MP
or three for good measure.
Set Windsor Castle ablaze in 1992.
- Your car bomber?
- This one likes to burn his victims alive.
Can't figure out how he does it either.
Not a crumb of evidence at the crime scene.
The last one died in his front garden...
...his poor wife watching helplessly
as he went up in smoke.
The Irish Republican Army?
Our suspect likes to send
love letters to his victims' wives.
Sent one to the wife of
Sir Malcolm Marsden a month ago.
Three days later he narrowly escaped
a fire in his garage, burned down.
So they're renting a place
out on Cape Cod...
...bringing the family
for an extended holiday.
- Or until we catch the dirty bugger.
- He's that determined?
Judging by his success, he takes
a certain delight in his work.
So what brings you on this detour
to Washington DC, Inspector?
I figured my friend Mulder...
...couldn't resist a three-pipe problem.
I'll run it by our arson specialist.
Splendid.
I'll call London, let them know.
Oh, goodbye.
Three-pipe problem?
- From Sherlock Holmes. It's a private joke.
- How private?
Um...
We knew each other at school in England.
She was brilliant and, uh...
I got in over my head and I... paid the price.
Mulder, you just keep unfolding
like a flower.
It was over ten years ago, Scully.
Yeah. You couldn't drop everything
fast enough to help her out.
I was merely extending her
a professional courtesy.
Oh, is that what you were extending?
I am going to run this by the arson guys,
then she's on her own.
Something tells me you're not
going to get rid of her that easily.
Beautiful!
Oh, just beautiful!
Look at that. Salmon-red flames.
This is 1400, 1500 degrees.
This is a work of art.
Was there any kind of
incendiary device used?
Yes, actually. The victim's body.
- Spontaneous combustion?
- He was murdered.
However, we've no evidence
that tells us how he caught fire.
That's peculiar.
People don't normally just catch on fire.
I mean, we burn,
but we don't conduct all that well.
There's usually some extraneous fuel
involved, like candle wax, gasoline...
...something flammable and
incendiary that adheres to skin.
- Like an accelerant?
- Like an accelerant! Yes!
But we found no trace,
save for magnesium at two sites.
That's alathactic pyrolysis,
a residue from an exothermic reaction.
There's no evidence of the source.
No pore pattern or ignition devices.
There have been some arson fires
in Seattle lately, and Pennsylvania.
They burn so hot the firemen
can't put them out. 7,000 degrees.
- Hosing that down makes it worse.
- How's that?
Well, the, uh... reaction is so intense...
...that it splits the water into hydrogen
and oxygen. Just adds fuel to the fire.
- What were they using?
- We don't know for sure.
Could be rocket fuel. That burns so hot
and clean there's never a trace left.
You see, it's very difficult to prove arson.
It's driving the insurance companies nuts.
That's about the only explanation
that I can give you.
There are cases of pyrokinetics,
people who can control and conduct fire.
Well, I've seen fire bend around corners.
I've seen it bounce like a rubber ball.
Fire's got a certain genius, you know...
...a certain... demon poetry.
It's like it's got a mind of its own.
But I've never seen one that can defy the
laws of physics. Not when you figure it out.
You've...
...got quite a case for yourself here, Mulder.
I almost wish I could be in your shoes.
Hey, Jackson!
- Boy, that's a nice house!
- What a pleasant surprise!
Welcome to America, Sir Malcolm.
In here, please.
And over there as well.
But the second one I want upstairs.
Gentlemen, the second set
of boxes will go directly up the stairs.
-  Hello there.
- Hello.
I'm Bob, the caretaker.
- We've been exchanging letters.
- Oh, hello, Bob!
Excuse the paint. Hi.
- Just trying to spruce the place up for you.
- Well, it's delightful.
- The photos don't do it justice.
- Anything I can do for you...
...anything at all, you just holler.
Thank you, Bob.
- He seems like a rather nice fellow.
- Very.
My God, darling!
That painting rather looks like you.
Do you think?
Oh, I don't know.
Bloody little cur! I'll skin you alive!
You see? I'm the caretaker now.
So, Sherlock, is the game afoot?
Afraid so, Watson.
But you're off the hook on this one.
What do you mean?
I'm not going to put you through this.
- Put me through what?
- Phoebe's little mind game.
What are you talking about?
There's something else
I haven't told you about myself, Scully.
I hate fire. Hate it.
I'm scared to death of it.
When I was a kid,
my best friend's house burned down.
I had to spend the night in the rubble,
to keep away looters.
For years I had nightmares about
being trapped in a burning building.
- And Phoebe knows about this?
- This is classic Phoebe Green.
Mind-game player extraordinaire.
Ten years, and then
she shows up with a case like this.
She shows up knowing the power she has
over you and makes you walk through fire.
Phoebe is fire.
Are you sure you don't want me
to help you out on this one?
Sooner or later,
a man's gotta face his demons.
Hello. You're the Marsdens' driver?
Who's that?
Bob.
The caretaker.
Oh. Yeah.
- Bum a smoke?
- Yeah, sure.
I'm going into town. Can I get you anything?
Some cough medicine, if it's no problem.
Syrup or... uh... lozenges?
Syrup'd be good.
Can I give you some money?
I appreciate that!
Beer.
They don't let you bring
your own around here.
I guess they'll just have
to make an exception... won't they?
You're English!
God, I just love that accent!
Allow me.
A gentleman, to boot.
Oh, my God!
Now, that is a trick!
Hey, guys! Take a look at this!
- Care for a light?
I pulled this report off the wire.
A customer in a bar caught fire,
but they're still looking for a body.
Any indication an accelerant was used?
The bar is across from a fire station.
Burned down before they could respond.
It turned the concrete foundation
into sponge cake.
This is a woman who was in the bar.
- Hello.
- Miss Gotchek?
- Yes.
I'm Special Agent Mulder from the FBI.
This is Inspector Green.
- Can you tell us what happened in the bar?
- There was this guy.
I'd had a few drinks, so...
He sat next to me and...
...he did this thing.
It was like a magic trick
where he lit his finger on fire.
When I turned around he was up in flames.
- Can you describe him?
- Good-looking, I think.
Brownish hair.
- Long hair? Short hair?
- I've already told the police.
Could you work with an artist
and come up with a sketch?
- I had a few drinks.
- Can I get your name and address?
See...
I live with someone.
- He thinks I was at school last night.
- It's no problem.
You can come down to the field office
and work with somebody.
I'll give you a minute to think about it, OK?
Deftly done, Agent Mulder.
Casually disregard her indiscretion.
Firm but polite until she co-operates.
A technique I refined in
my relationship with you.
Oh. I see you haven't lost
your sense of humour.
I'm sorry. That was a cheap shot.
I don't want to dredge up the past.
- Let's just stick to the case.
- Let's.
- Look, Phoebe...
- Unless I'm mistaken...
...ten years seems time
to have forgiven if not forgotten...
- ..a few youthful indiscretions.
- I'm cursed with a photographic memory.
Then don't you tell me
that you've forgotten...
...a certain youthful indiscretion...
...atop Sir Arthur Conan Doyle's tombstone...
...on a misty night in Windlesham.
Like I said, let's just stick to the case.
It occurred to me that
we're going to a lot of trouble...
...to find the description of a man
who was burnt to a crisp.
I would agree,
but they haven't found a body yet.
So, can we count on you?
Yeah. OK.
I don't know if it matters...
...but I remembered something else
about the guy who caught fire.
He had an English accent.
Having a rough time, huh?
Maybe it's the cough syrup.
After reviewing the files of
the Scotland Yard arson murders...
..two points remain unexplained.
One is the use of an untraceable accelerant.
The other involves the victims.
Since they all burned in the presence
of family members in safe surroundings...
..this indicates unusually intimate access
to the victims by the arsonist.
The arsonist is most likely a male,
less than 25 years of age.
He will often act out of impulse...
..satisfying sexual urges or insecurities
with destructive behaviour...
.. which compensates for social
inadequacies or maladjustment.
- You boys want to see a magic trick?
- OK.
- What's your names?
- Michael. And Jimmie.
- Doesn't he talk?
- Yes!
- What kind of magic trick?
- Maybe I'd better not.
- Show us!
- You might tell your mom and dad.
- We won't tell.
- Really?
- Promise?
- Promise.
Hope to die? Stick a needle in your eye?
OK, boys. You've taken the solemn oath
of trust that can't be broken...
...except... under penalty...
...of death.
Watch.
- Is it in there?
- No.
Ah! You're too smart for me!
- Where did it go?
- Where do you think, Jimmie?
- I don't know.
Uh...
I think I remember.
Ah... ah... ah!
Da-da!
- Do it again!
- You want me to do it again?
OK. I'll do it again.
Agent Beatty?
I'm Special Agent Dana Scully.
- Can I steal a minute of your time?
- Yeah, sure.
Come in. I'm just working on
this Mafia torch job here.
I'm... working with Agent Mulder.
Oh, yeah. Wild case.
So, what can I do for you?
You said the arsonist might be using
some kind of rocket fuel as an accelerant.
Just speculation. It doesn't explain
how he sets bodies on fire.
What if he got some of this fuel into some...
...hand cream, or...
Well, you've got to understand that...
...even the smallest amounts of this stuff can
produce temperatures over 5,000 degrees.
But I suppose it's not impossible.
Extremely diluted.
He'd still have to find a way to ignite it.
Wow! It lit by itself!
Come on. Sit down.
So...
- You guys ever smoked a cigarette?
- No, they're bad for you.
Would you like a puff, Michael?
- No.
- Make a man out of you.
- I don't want to.
- Why don't you hold one for me?
How about you, Jimmie?
Huh? Little man?
Jimmie! Michael!
Hello.
Bob... Ugh!
We've had a bit of bad news.
Our driver has taken ill and we're due
at a party in Boston this evening.
Is there any chance that we can impose
upon you to drive the family into town?
We'd be happy to pay you for your time
and put you up for the night.
- I'd be very happy to do it as a favour.
- Good. Thank you.
Boys, let's go. Daddy's got lunch all ready.
The arsonist is usually unmarried
and prone to obsessive fantasies...
..about women or men inaccessible to him.
The setting of fires
results from his cowardice...
..and inability to develop
a natural relationship.
His crimes are often very clever
and elaborately planned.
The suspicious nature of the fire
last night strongly suggests...
..the arsonist has followed
Lord Marsden to the United States.
A check of all recent immigration
to the northeastern area is under way.
It has become not a matter of if...
..but when he will strike.
- Here's that immigration data you wanted.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
Remember those reports about people
who can control and conduct fire?
- Vaguely.
- This guy just told us he's far more exotic.
I should say so, if he can set himself on fire.
- What?
- I'm not used to someone so quick to agree.
- Oh.
- What protection does the family have?
The driver's a very capable bodyguard.
He should get more men and limit exposure.
There's a party
in their honour tonight in Boston.
- They'll have to cancel.
- Unless you want to set a trap.
I had thought of that...
...but we must be careful and discreet.
The party's at eight, at the Venable Plaza.
I'll travel with the family.
Why don't you go on ahead
and have a look around?
Oh, and I've taken a room
at the hotel for the night.
Thanks.
Thank you.
- Mulder.
- It's Scully. Where are you?
- I'm in Boston.
- I've got something to show you.
- I'm going to come up there.
- What have you got?
I might have information on
the identity of your arsonist.
- Are you there, Mulder?
- Yeah.
- Can I meet you somewhere?
It's just that I'm kind of
anticipating having my hands full.
Hey! We're here!
- Phoebe.
- Thank you.
- Evening, sir.
- Hello.
Enjoying yourself?
Good food, witty conversation...
I'm having the time of my life.
I wondered if you think it's safe enough
to indulge ourselves in a dance.
It doesn't look like your arsonist
is going to make an appearance.
That doesn't mean
there won't be any fires to put out.
I've thought about you often.
There's a fire upstairs!
- What?
- On the 14th floor.
That's where the children are.
You've got a fire on the 14th floor!
Help us!
Here we go! We got one down!
Come on, buddy! Come on!
- Can you walk?
- I got him.
- Here we are.
- Jimmie! Michael!
You saved their lives!
- Who is he?
- He's the driver.
Well done! Good job.
You were really out.
- Where's Phoebe?
- She's down the hall.
- What about the kids?
- OK. The doctor checked them out.
What happened to you up there?
I panicked. Couldn't move, Scully.
It could have happened to anyone.
Yeah. But it happened to me.
I haired out.
Plain and simple.
What do you know about this guy
that saved the kids? The driver?
I checked him out
prior to the Marsdens' arrival.
He's worked on the property
for eight years. No record.
His references checked out.
They were lucky he was here.
- Who was watching the kids tonight?
- He was.
I could have sworn I saw him in the hall
about the time the fire broke out.
You couldn't have.
Anyway, our suspect is English.
Hey.
I came to see if you were OK.
- How are the kids?
- They're fine.
Everybody's anxious to get back.
- To the Cape?
- Only to pack.
They're travelling back to England
the day after tomorrow.
And you?
I'll be leaving in a few days.
I'll give you a ring
back at the Bureau before I leave.
Goodbye.
Are you OK?
Yeah.
Are you at all interested in what
I came all the way up here to show you?
Yeah.
Well, I did some checking on my own.
I didn't know a whole lot about arson
or arsonists, so I took the opportunity.
For my own edification, of course.
I ran a profile of possible
incendiary fuels and accelerants...
...that could have been used in the crimes.
I also took the liberty of running
a search through Interpol...
...of all the gardeners and domestic help
that were hired by the murder victims.
- And?
- And...
These people probably don't
even tie their own shoes.
There were over 200 names...
...and not a duplicate... except one.
A Cecil Lively.
He worked as a gardener
for two of the victims.
- What did you find on him?
- Nothing.
- So he's clean?
- Apparently...
...he was questioned by Scotland Yard
and they released him.
But I dug a little further.
Cecil Lively is a documented
citizen of Great Britain.
Paid his taxes, never been on the dole...
A model citizen.
Until he died in 1971 in
a London tenement fire.
I know. That's what I thought.
So, I checked a little further.
Cecil L'lvely, spelled L apostrophe,
came up again. In fact, it came up twice.
On a list of death certificates, among
children who died in ritual sacrifice...
...by a satanic cult in 1963 in the
Tautingham Woods outside Bath, England.
- Where else did you find it?
- You're gonna love this.
On a list of recent visas issued
by the British Government.
Cecil L'lvely's passport was
stamped by US Immigration...
...two weeks ago in Boston.
Call the local field office in Boston
of the FBI and get them to fax you...
...the composite the witness did.
Fax it to every local
law enforcement agency.
- What are you gonna do?
- Try and catch Phoebe.
This guy could be waiting
for them at Cape Cod.
Yes. This is Special Agent Scully.
I've been waiting on hold for you guys
to fax me a composite of an arson suspect.
Right. Hang on a second.
It's coming through. Thanks.
Oh, my God!
It's the driver.
The cellular customer you are
trying to reach is out of the area.
Excuse me.
His name is Cecil L'lvely.
- Who?
- Your arsonist.
Where's the rest of the family?
- They went outside for a walk.
- Well, go find them.
We've got to get them packed
and out of here.
Come on, hurry! Let's go!
It's the driver.
I know. He disappeared.
What's the matter?
Nothing. Um...
I found this out in the garage...
It's been very hard on the family.
Did you get the composite?
- Yes.
- I don't believe it. I can't believe it.
- He's worked for us for over ten years.
- Obviously there's been some mistake.
Oh.
Oh, my God!
- This isn't the driver! It's the caretaker!
- He's upstairs with the children!
Michael!
Jimmie!
Looks like we've found the missing driver.
Mulder! In here, quickly!
- What's going on?!
- They just went off - all by themselves!
My God!
- Oh, my God!
- Everybody out!
- I think he rigged the whole house.
- Oh, no!
It's fuel.
Go! Go!
Come on! Move! Move!
Scully, find a fire extinguisher.
- Everybody else, out!
- What about the children?
I'll take care of the children.
Go!
- Are you going to be OK, Mulder?
- Oh, yeah. I'll be fine.
There's no place I'd rather be.
Michael! Jimmie!
Are you in there?
Help!
Time to call 911?
Don't move!
Freeze!
Federal Agent.
You won't shoot me.
Stay right where you are!
See?
Cos you don't know...
...the spark from that round...
...won't blow this whole house
to kingdom come.
Aagh!
Back off, Scully! It's the accelerant!
Someone help us!
- Oh, my boys! My babies!
- Michael! Jimmie! Thank God! Thank God!
You can't kill me!
You can't fight fire...
...with fire!
Care to take me to lunch?
Scare you?
You have no idea.
Where is Phoebe?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
- She didn't call?
- No.
- She did messenger this to me last night.
- Did you play it?
- No.
- Why not?
Aren't you curious what's on it?
Ten to one you can't dance to it.
Χ-File number 11214893.
Addendum to the file opened
by Special Agent Mulder.
The arson suspect, Cecil L'lvely,
was admitted to Boston Mercy Hospital...
.. with fifth and sixth degree
burns over his entire body.
Military burns specialists have been...
..brought in to study the case,
which they're calling extraordinary...
..as the suspect not only survived,
but also had rapid regeneration
of his basal cell tissue.
Full recovery is anticipated
in as little as a month.
L'lvely is being held
in a high-security medical facility,
confined to a hyperbaric chamber...
..until he can be tried for the murder
of a Massachusetts caretaker.
His body temperature remains
at a steady 109 degrees.
Health technicians have removed
anything flammable from his room...
.. due to several fires in the vicinity.
According to Agent Mulder,
further incarceration...
..remains a problem for
federal penal authorities.
Can I get you anything, sir?
I'm just dying for a cigarette.
I made this!