Lauren, I've been looking every...
Are you all right?
- Do you want some water or...
- No, I-I'm fine.
Oh, honey...
...it's been a couple of weeks now.
- Do you wanna talk?
- No.
Really, Jane, I'm OK. I just haven't
known a lot of people who've died.
I've never known anybody
that killed themselves.
Oh, well, maybe once everything
gets packed away...
...it'll get easier, there won't be
the constant reminder.
Here's your paycheque.
Oh, come on... go home.
OK.
Ahh!
I have no money!
Ahh! No, let me go!
No!
Ugh!
I think I'll pass.
Hey, I know a good place to crash.
Up the fire escape...
...through that window.
Come on, I'll give you a boost.
Pull it down.
- I can't get it down.
- Come on, pull!
- Come on!
Hurry up!
Agent Scully, Agent Mulder.
Chief Blevins assures us
of your cooperation.
We regret any inconvenience.
We hope your expertise
in extraordinary phenomenon...
...will help us answer some questions.
You're not FBI, are you?
Have you ever analysed
anything like this before?
Abnormal postmortem muscle reflex.
Both corpses are still responding
to exposure to high levels...
...of electrostatic charge.
Any external lesions or surface burns?
- None.
- Time of death?
Well, it can't be long. The body's still warm.
Somatic death occurred
sometime over six hours ago...
...but their body temperatures
have yet to drop below 98.3 degrees.
Where did you find them?
Tell us the time and mode of transport.
It might help us determine
why the bodies haven't cooled.
Hey, you guys called us down here.
You want some answers,
you gotta give some.
They travelled 60 minutes by air.
Thank you.
The most troubling aspect
of the deaths is the throat area.
Larynx, oesophagus and hyoid bone
were crushed like chalk.
There's no abrasions...
...or evidence of tissue damage.
It's as if their throats were crushed...
...from the inside.
Who are these guys?
If you've done your examinations,
why are you consulting us?
During your work on the X-Files,
ever seen anything like this?
No, never.
Thank you very much for your time,
Agent Mulder, Scully.
If any inquiry as to this meeting
be made, we request full denial.
I'd say you people already suffer
from full denial.
You lied.
You have seen it before, I can tell.
You lied to them.
I would never lie.
I wilfully participated
in a campaign of misinformation.
Who do you think they were?
NSA, CIA, some organisation
Congress will uncover in the next scandal.
But what's important is what they have.
They have no idea because they called us in.
I have X-Files. Each case
has an element of what we saw.
Electrostatic charge, internal mutilation
with no external causality.
None has all the elements in one case.
How can an oesophagus be crushed
without the neck being touched?
Psychokinetic manipulation.
Psychokinesis?
You mean,
how Carrie got even at the prom?
The Russians were doing studies on it.
The Chinese still are.
Their findings are kept secret.
OK, I'm intrigued.
But how can we investigate?
We have nothing to go on.
Just getting in, Lauren?
Oh! Yes.
Mr Graves used to let you get away
with that, but Mr Dorlund is in charge now.
I wondered if I could have
a minute with him.
Tomorrow...
...at three.
Can I see him today? It's really important.
Is everything all right out here?
- Can I speak with you?
- Mm.
Please.
Um... I'm here to give my two-week notice.
Ah.
Lauren, Jane told me about you crying
in Howard's office...
...and I... I want you to know
you're not alone.
As a matter of fact...
...we share something special.
Howard and I started this company
ten years ago...
...and as long as I knew him, he had
no interest in anything but work...
...and so some of us became family.
I was his brother and
you were like a daughter to him...
...so, of course, I feel very close to you.
And I...
I wanna take care of my family.
Stay, Lauren, please.
The company needs you...
...especially now.
I won't let you leave!
What's wrong?
I... uh... I can't. I have to leave.
I... I can't be here anymore.
You've got two weeks.
Mohammed Amrollahi.
Illegal possession of firearms...
...illegal possession of explosives,
falsification of export licences.
He has ties to an exiled
extremist group - the Isfahan.
Named after a city in Iran, they've
been working out of Philadelphia...
That's 60 air minutes.
I'll talk to the Philly PD.
It was last Wednesday night.
I was just on routine patrol.
This is where we found 'em.
- Who discovered their bodies?
- Nobody.
It was about 10. I was on patrol.
Saw them hangin' around.
No witnesses?
The people that come here
after business hours...
...don't witness very much,
know what I'm sayin'?
- I appreciate your help.
A daily visual record is made
of everyone who makes a transaction.
We'll just have to question everyone...
...who was at the machine
before 10 that night.
There. Back up.
"Lauren Kyte, 858 Franklin, Bensalem."
Why would the Isfahan rob someone
of 40 bucks at an ATM machine?
Look at that!
Maybe it's another person.
Maybe... maybe not.
Well, the resolution's too poor.
It won't help much to enhance it.
That leaves us only one person
we know we can talk to.
Come on.
Hello?
Ms Lauren Kyte, please.
I'm Agent Fox Mulder,
this is Agent Dana Scully.
We're with the FBI.
Do you mind if we come in?
- I was just in the middle of...
- Thank you. We won't be long.
Ever seen either of these two men before?
No.
Take your time.
I-I'm sorry, I've never seen them before.
I'm afraid you have.
It's a surveillance picture from your ATM.
Can you tell us what happened that night?
Um...
These guys...
I-I was depositing my paycheque...
...they grabbed me, I got away, I ran.
I-I just didn't wanna file a report.
They were found dead.
Have you ever seen this person before?
No.
I'm sorry, I can't tell you.
Does that mean you know?
Uh... It-it means I...
I can't tell you who it is.
When you can tell me...
...this is a number
I can be reached at any time.
- OK?
- Mm-hm.
A woman her size breaking free
and outrunning those men?
Then somehow crushing their necks?
She knows who the other person is.
She's packing, running away. From what?
What's happening?
What the hell's going on?
Hang on!
You OK?
Yeah.
Hi.
Hi. Paramedics check you out?
I'm fine, though I have
a standing-in-line-at-the-DMV-sized
headache.
Mine's more IRS-sized.
- They check out the car?
- Yeah. It's brand-new, only 100 miles.
Then someone tampered with it
while we were in her house.
Mechanic says everything's in order -
nothing cut, nothing greased.
Check out the lights.
They're on.
No, the filaments are heated due to
huge levels of electrostatic charge...
...like the bodies in the morgue.
Isn't it interesting that Lauren Kyte...
...was present both times?
She was with us the entire time
we were at her house.
What if it's possible somehow to raise
the body's electrostatic charge...
...to the levels we've seen
and use that energy to affect objects?
If a person could generate
that much energy...
...their body would break down,
they'd start glowing.
There's evidence in the X-Files -
furniture moving untouched...
...objects levitating,
unexplained electrical discharges.
Frequently, people with
psychokinetic power...
...are unaware of their own capability.
Are you saying Lauren Kyte crashed our car?
Either that... or a poltergeist.
- They're here!
- They may be.
Oh, come on, Mulder,
look at the tangible evidence.
Two Mid-East extremists were killed...
...trying to assault a woman working for...
...a manufacturer of parts
for the Defense Department.
When we questioned her,
our car was sabotaged.
Someone else may have
committed both acts.
Maybe the same someone
we saw in the ATM photos.
The mystery isn't psychokinetic energy...
...it's her accomplice.
Excuse me, sir...
She's clean.
No arrests, not even a traffic ticket.
Only thing is, she's in deep
with her credit card company. $15,000.
What do you think you're doing?
What are you doing? No, no.
I'll take care of this, all right?
Just go!
Here. I-I'll talk to someone.
A little upset over losing
a parking space, wouldn't you say?
So who is Howard Graves, anyway?
She was his secretary.
That's three people dead in the last month...
...associated with Lauren Kyte.
You won't find too many people
at their boss's grave...
...who aren't dancing on it.
Look at this one.
Excuse me.
Sir, is there an office
where I can get some information...
...on those people?
Who?
I attend every funeral.
I'm the last person to see them put to rest.
Do you know how Sarah Lynn
was related to Howard Graves?
His daughter.
They were at home one day...
...and he didn't latch the pool gate.
She drowned.
His wife left him a year later.
She's buried in a plot
in the northeast corner.
Thank you, sir.
You're welcome.
She was only three years old.
If she'd lived, she'd be Lauren's age.
Further investigation
into Lauren's history...
..reveals an estrangement from her family.
Phone records confirm no contact
with her parents for two years.
Her actions, during surveillance,
indicate a strong relationship...
..between Lauren and her employer,
the late Howard Graves.
Did this relationship
somehow motivate his suicide?
How are the attack...
..and the subsequent murders
of the Isfahan agents related, if at all?
I am certain the answers
to these questions...
..lie in finding the identify
of Lauren's accomplice.
Enhance it by 10.
That's Howard Graves.
He's alive.
Not necessarily.
No... No!
Stop!
Don't do this to me!
Howard?
No!
No! Stop!
No, no!
Please, no!
Howard!
They killed him!
I think Howard Graves
fabricated his own death.
Do you know how difficult it is
to fake your own death?
Only one man has pulled it off - Elvis!
He and Lauren are in on something.
Maybe an illegal dealing,
something the CIA was interested in.
You may be right.
Wait!
You think I'm right?
Sure. All you gotta do is prove
Howard Graves is still alive.
Howard Graves is very dead.
May we see the autopsy report, please?
Knock yourself out.
"Cause of death - arterial haemorrhage."
Four out of six litres of blood...
...down the tub.
There seems to be some blood work
missing here.
We only do that if we suspect homicide.
I don't suppose you ran
dental confirmations?
- What for? It was him.
- How did you know?
It said so on the toe tag.
Who made positive ID on the body?
Lauren Kyte.
But Graves was cremated.
There's no way to run a dental check
or get a DNA sample.
Yes, there is. His body's tissues
and organs were donated.
Howard Graves is in five different people.
They harvested the organs
immediately after death.
His kidneys went to Boston, his liver
to Dallas and his corneas to Oregon.
They've all been transplanted.
We cryo-preserved the dura mater -
the membrane of the spinal column.
We have Graves' hospital records.
We'll extract a sample and, in two hours...
...confirm the identity of the donor.
I, uh, made them rush...
...so you could have your cheque
before you leave.
Aw, I'm gonna miss you.
Aw, what?
Here.
Bye.
You were gonna leave
without saying goodbye?
Well, uh, I came to say goodbye...
...and to wish you luck.
And to leave you with this little thought.
I know Howard told you...
...and if it ever gets out...
...I won't waste my time
trying to pin the source.
I'll go straight to you.
And you'll do to me
what you did to Howard?
- I know you had him killed.
- Why would you say that?
He told me.
Mulder.
Lauren Kyte.
How soon can you be at my house?
- Why?
- Please hurry.
The tests are conclusive.
The dura mater does belong to Graves.
He is indeed very dead.
Just a second.
- Go run the bath.
- Get out of here!
No!
- No, no!
No-o-o-o-o-o!
No-o-o-o!
Stop!
Sto-o-op! No!
You know, you're not under arrest.
You're just here for questioning.
The sooner you talk to us...
...the sooner you get to go home.
What happened to those people tonight?
Do you have any idea who they might be?
Why did they attack you?
Do you know who this is?
Scully, Mulder.
He'll keep an eye on her. Come on. Now.
You've seriously compromised
our investigation.
We followed leads pertaining to an X-File.
I wanna know every detail
concerning this case.
What case? You withheld information.
Why not tell us what you've got?
Then we have nothing more to talk about.
Wait.
HTG Industrial Technologies sold
restricted parts to the Isfahan.
Serial numbers were recovered
in the July bombing of a navy transport van.
- How was Lauren involved?
- We don't know.
You impeded our investigation.
We don't have enough evidence to hold her.
If she doesn't talk, she goes free.
We lose our chance to break this.
I could make her talk.
My advice to you...
...don't get rough with her.
That was a waste of time.
Your turn.
- Lauren...
- I won't talk to you either.
OK... then you're free to go.
I can't go back to that house.
Why?
Because of Howard Graves?
- He's dead.
- I know.
He's watching over you, isn't he?
I don't know if you've ever been
a secretary before.
Sometimes your boss can talk
as if you weren't even in the room...
...which can hurt, you know.
But sometimes...
you're all he has to talk to...
...which was how it always was
with me and Howard.
One night, late, I went into his office.
He was crying. More scared than sad.
Pentagon contracts were being cancelled...
...the company was going under.
He felt personally responsible
for each of his employees.
Seeing and feeling their fear every day...
...really wore him down.
And this one time...
...Dorlund came with that group,
that... um... Mid-East group.
Isfahan.
That terrorist group.
They buy parts at an outrageous price.
Not just once, but for as long as
they could get away with it.
That night Howard was crying.
He'd found out
Isfahan had claimed responsibility...
...for killing a couple of sailors in Florida.
He was never the same...
...and I thought...
that's why he killed himself.
But he didn't.
I saw...
Howard showed me
how Dorlund had him killed.
Made it look like a suicide.
He could see Howard
was gonna put an end to the deal.
So now Howard is protecting you?
- It sounds so ridiculous.
- But you believe it.
He was closer to me than my father.
I told him that.
I still feel his presence.
Sometimes...
...I even smell his aftershave.
If you just could've...
...seen...
...the things I've seen.
But I just... want all that to go away.
That's why I'm leaving.
Maybe he can move on.
That's not enough.
You have been given the chance
to tell him again.
Take it.
Tell him you love him...
by showing him, by...
...by helping us finish
his unfinished business.
Lauren...
...how will you ever be able to rest
if he never can?
OK.
I'm a mess.
I'm gonna... um... freshen up.
What are you doing, Scully?
You don't believe.
Mulder, there's no such thing
as ghosts or psychokinesis.
I'm sure there's an explanation,
but I believe she believes.
My priority is to get her
to help us stop Dorlund.
We may have just sacrificed our best chance
to observe spectral phenomena.
No, I'm giving us the chance
to solve a case that's tangible...
...instead of chasing after shadows.
- Get in line!
- Yes, sir.
You ready?
All right, everyone. We have
a warrant to search the premises...
...for evidence pertaining
to the sale of restricted parts.
Evidence may be in the form
of falsified export licences...
...parts manifests, communiqués.
If could be on computer disk or hard copy.
If in doubt, ask. We need this to be clean.
This is the culmination
of a year-long investigation.
If we don't come out with something
proving a link to the Isfahan...
...this guy could walk.
OK, let's go!
You OK?
It'll most likely be in Dorlund's office.
We'll execute the search...
...but we'll need you to guide us
so you'll have to be strong, OK?
Everybody, stay calm.
Federal Bureau of Investigation.
Ma'am, could you back away
from those files, please?
Step aside, please.
This is all we could find.
We don't have him.
He's not even breaking a sweat.
Our case is blown. We wasted a year.
This guy is gonna walk.
Let's get outta here.
Lauren, it's over.
We have to go.
What we're looking for isn't here.
Look, she's no agent.
I don't want to be combative, but
she has no right to destroy my property!
Destroying property? What about that van
that blew up killing those men?!
What are you talking about,
you stupid bitch?
Lauren, no!
Don't kill him!
Help us find it!
Get down!
Mulder!
Oh, my God!
I guess
what we're looking for is here.
The US Attorney is going after Dorlund
with all he's got...
...including the murder of Howard Graves.
I'll come back to testify.
Where are you going?
Away from here.
Thanks.
Boy, she's in a rush to get outta here.
Out of here or away from
the ghost of Howard Graves?
Hey, Scully, do you believe in an afterlife?
I'd settle for a life in this one.
Have you ever seen the Liberty Bell?
Yes.
I've been to Philly a hundred times
and never seen it.
You're not missing much. It's a big bell with
a crack and you have to wait in a long line.
Yeah, but I'd really like to go.
Why now?
I don't know. How late
do you think they stay open?
Miss Kyte, I asked for this 25 minutes ago.
I know. I'm sorry.
Maybe that's the way they work back East.
Here punctuality is a virtue.
We have to find new office space -
every time a truck goes by...
...the whole building shakes!
That's all, Lauren.
Pam Atkinson
I made this!