What's she doing there by herself?
Tina?
Honey?
You're freezing. Where's your jacket?
Where's your daddy?
In the yard. He told me
he needed some time to himself.
I'd say his time's up.
Come on, honey, I'm sure
he wouldn't want you to catch cold.
Joel?
Hey, Joel, the swing set's supposed
to be for your daughter, not you!
I'll call 911.
Daddy?
Death by hypovolemia.
75% blood loss.
That's over four litres of blood.
You could say
the man was running on empty.
The man's daughter, eight years old...
...was away from his side
for no more than 10 minutes.
She doesn't remember anything.
There was no trace evidence.
It would've been washed away
by yesterday's rain.
There were two puncture wounds
in the jugular.
Are you familiar
with the phenomenon of cattle mutilations?
Hmm?
Since 1967...
...over 34 states have reported
unsolved cases of cattle mutilation.
The trace evidence is remarkably similar.
Incision marks of surgical precision.
The area around the mouth and often
the sexual organs has been removed.
There's substantial blood loss...
...with no blood at the scene.
- How can that be?
- Exsanguination.
If you stuck a needle in the jugular,
the heart itself would act as a pump.
These animals
had their jugulars punctured...
...in the same way as the man
from Connecticut.
It's the first time
I've ever seen it on a human.
There was no sign of a struggle.
How can a man sit through a blood-letting?
The ME found digitalis...
...a South American plant
that can be used as a paralytic drug.
These X-Files indicate
this is a UFO-related phenomenon.
Often there are sightings nearby,
surface burns.
Witnesses report time loss,
as in abduction cases.
That might explain why
the girl remembers nothing.
Why would aliens
travel light years to Earth...
...in order to play doctor on cattle?
For the same reason
we cut up frogs and monkeys.
Besides...
...they seem to have
stepped up their interest.
Her mother passed away
from ovarian cancer two years ago.
There's no other family.
We'll keep Tina here until we can
place her with a foster family.
- Has she spoken about it?
- No, not a word.
- Any nightmares?
- No. At least not that I know of.
- Can we talk to her now?
- Yes.
Tina...
...these are the people we talked about.
This is Miss Scully and Mr Mulder.
Do you think you can talk to them?
OK.
Hi.
I know you must be feeling
very sad right now.
And scared.
But we wanna find out what happened
so we can help stop...
...whoever hurt your daddy, OK?
OK.
Did you ever see any strangers
with your daddy at home?
Did you ever see anyone
yell at your daddy...
...or your daddy yell at them?
No.
Can you think of anyone
who might wanna hurt him?
No.
That's a nice bunny, Tina.
Can we talk about what happened that day?
About what happened
in the back yard. Yeah?
Do you remember
any strange sounds or lights...
...or anything like that?
There was red lightning.
Can you tell me more
about the red lightning?
I can't remember.
It... all went dark.
Have you ever seen
anything like that before?
You have? When?
The men from the clouds -
they were after my dad.
Scully.
- Where?
- Why were these men after your dad?
They wanted to exsanguinate him.
Thanks. Mulder.
What?
There's been another one.
It's like looking at a mirror image.
"The victim, Doug Reardon,
was married with one daughter."
"Cause of death - hypovolemia."
Mulder, this is uncanny.
They also found traces
of the poison digitalis.
- Puncture wound?
- Uh... yes.
On the jugular.
Time of death was estimated at 2.30pm.
The same day, only three hours earlier
than the Simmons murder.
That's Pacific Standard Time.
That makes it the exact same moment.
It appears we've two serial killers
working in tandem.
No, serial killers rarely work in pairs.
When they do, they kill together,
not separately.
Nothing beyond
your leading questions to Tina...
...substantiates a UFO mutilation theory.
Was Reardon's daughter here
when he was murdered?
Yes.
The police report states
that she remembers nothing.
Uh, she's with her mother and family
in Sacramento.
- When will they be back?
- Um... tomorrow.
Even money she'll remember red lightning.
Tina?
Tina!
She was kidnapped from the Social Services
home at 11pm last night.
Looks like someone was afraid
she might remember too much.
Someone or something, Scully.
Connecticut state troopers set up
roadblocks within half an hour.
Nothing.
Maybe they weren't looking
in the right direction!
I told them to contact us
in case they find her.
Tina?
No.
Wh-What's your name?
Cindy Reardon.
Do you live here, Cindy?
Ever since I was born - eight years ago.
Ahhhh!
This is the ceremonial signing...
Cindy really is a beautiful
little girl, Mrs Reardon.
Doug and I wanted to spoil her.
We wanted to protect her from
everything horrible in the world.
- She was daddy's little girl.
- Is she an only child?
May I ask... was Cindy adopted?
No!
I gave birth to her...
...at San Rafael General.
I assume you have the documentation,
birth certificate...
- Of course I do.
- Was she the only child delivered?
What the hell kind of question is that?
Look, I have told the police
everything I know.
Mrs Reardon,
have you ever seen this man before?
Is this your suspect?
- No.
- Did he do something to Cindy?
- No, h-he...
- No.
Mrs Reardon...
...this is not your daughter.
That girl's name is Tina Simmons.
She lives 3,000 miles away
in Greenwich, Connecticut.
That man, her father, was killed
in the same way as your husband.
Cindy is my daughter.
I can show you videos of her birth.
We tried for six years to become pregnant.
In vitro fertilisation?
- At which clinic?
- Luther Stapes Center...
...down in San Francisco.
Do you still believe...
...this is UFO related?
- Cindy didn't see red lightning.
- I don't know.
The only thing similar about these girls
seems to be their appearance.
There is the possibility
they have an unrelated likeness.
Both just happen to see
their fathers exsanguinated.
I'd like to get the odds on that in Vegas!
The girls are the one and only link
between identical murders.
- And one girl was just abducted.
- Kidnapped.
Potato, po-tah-to
Where are you going?
If the murders were committed
by the same person...
...part of the pattern is
kidnapping the daughter.
You expect the pattern to continue.
I'll keep an eye on the girl.
Check out the clinic.
See if the Simmons
were in the same programme.
I'll call the San Francisco Bureau
and get someone to relieve you.
OK.
In vitro fertilisation is a procedure
in which we implement fertilisation...
...and implantation of the embryo
in the uterus.
Could a patient believe
she was receiving her own egg...
...but receive another without knowing?
Not here. We have very strict controls.
Have you ever had patients
named Claudia and Joel Simmons?
Any patient information is confidential.
It's our policy.
The Simmons are dead.
Their daughter has been kidnapped.
I'd say any information that could help
would override your policy.
You had copies of their records...
...transferred to Greenwich,
Connecticut in 1991.
They came here nine years ago under
the supervision of a Dr Sally Kendrick?
Is there a problem?
Dr Kendrick was nothing but a problem.
Hello. Welcome to the Luther Stapes Center
for Reproductive Medicine.
I'm Dr Sally Kendrick...
..a specialist in the exciting field
of in vitro fertilisation.
She was a resident here in 1985.
Brilliant.
First in her class at Yale Med
where she got her MD...
...after completing her doctorate
in biogenetics.
We were thrilled to get her.
And now you don't sound so thrilled.
We have reason to believe...
...Dr Kendrick was tampering with
the genetic material of fertilised ova...
...in the lab prior to implant.
Experimenting with eugenics.
- Did you report this to the AMA?
- Of course.
I fired her. I also requested an investigation
from the US Health Department.
- And what happened?
- The AMA censured her.
My request for an investigation was denied.
Dr Kendrick... disappeared.
We know the pain
of infertility, and we are ready to help.
In the next half-hour...
Kendrick was
the supervising physician...
...in the Reardons'
and the Simmons' IVF programme.
It seems she was experimenting
at the clinic.
And maybe now
she's trying to erase the results?
..But with our scientific advances,
a little luck and a lot of hope...
..miracles can happen.
She must've had an accomplice...
...to have done both murders.
You think this is a vendetta she
and a colleague have against the Center?
Does this mean you've abandoned
your UFO connection?
- Hello?
Hello?
Just a couple of clicks.
Must be a wrong number.
I tell you what, I'm gonna sleep on it...
...and we'll talk about it in the morning.
Mulder, you're rushing me out of the room.
No, I'm not.
- Do you have a girl coming over?
- What's a girl?
I got a movie I wanna watch on TV.
Sleep tight. I'll see you in the morning.
Are you certain she hasn't followed you?
Yes. What are you doing here?
Well, I thought we might
take in a Warriors game.
Actually, I was... uh...
...just in the neighbourhood and...
...wondered if I had ever told you
about the Litchfield experiments.
Hmm.
No, you haven't.
Well, it was a most... interesting project.
Highest level of classification,
all records have since been destroyed...
...and those who knew of it...
...will deny knowledge of its existence.
In the early '50s,
during the height of the Cold War...
...we got wind the Russians were
fooling around with eugenics.
Rather primitively, I might add.
Trying to cross-breed top scientists,
athletes, you name it...
...to come up with the superior soldier.
Naturally, we jumped on the bandwagon.
The Litchfield experiment.
Mm-hm. A group
of genetically controlled children...
.. were raised and monitored
on a compound in Litchfield.
The boys were called Adam...
..and the girls were called... Eve.
There's a woman you should see...
..and I'll make sure that you can get in.
Agents Mulder and Scully here to see Eve 6.
Deposit your firearms.
- Sign for these.
- What are those?
Panic buttons.
I can't let you inside without one.
Whaddaya want?
Why the flashlight?
She screams and screams
if we turn the overheads on.
No-one's ever got a good look at her.
We'll be right outside.
Hello?
So, I guess you've found
what you're looking for.
One of us, at least.
Sally Kendrick.
Unlock the chains, then we'll talk.
Probably there for a good reason.
No... a bad reason.
I paid too much attention to a guard.
Bit into his eyeball!
I meant it as a sign of affection.
You here to give me an IQ test,
by any chance?
I think I can top 265.
We're very bright, we Eves.
It runs in the family.
Where are the others -
the Adams and the Eves?
We're prone to suicide.
All that's left is me...
...and Eve 7 - she escaped early on.
Eve 8, she escaped 10 years later.
Are you Sally Kendrick?
That's not my name...
...but... she is me and I am her...
...and we are all together!
Did you work for
the Luther Stapes Center in 1985?
In 1985...
...I'd been tied up like this for two years!
And for what reason?
No reason! I did nothing!
I'm just me!
They made me, but did they suffer?
No, no, I suffer!
I suffer!
They keep me alive...
...for the Litchfield Project!
They come in, they test me...
...they poke me to see what went wrong!
Sally knows what went wrong.
You and you...
...you have 46 chromosomes.
The Adams made the Eves.
We have 56.
We have extra chromosomes.
Number 4, 512, 16 and 22.
This replication of chromosomes
also produces additional genes.
Heightened strength...
...heightened intelligence...
Heightened psychosis.
Saved the best for last.
You don't believe me.
I have proof. Look on my wall.
My family album.
My God, it's the girls!
We were close...
...we were very close!
Sally Kendrick was using the clinic
to carry on the Litchfield experiment.
She was cloning herself.
Now I lay me down to sleep...
...I pray the Lord my soul to keep.
If I should die before I wake...
...I pray the Lord my soul to take.
God bless Grandma and Grandpa Stenner...
...Irma and Irmapop...
...and God bless Mom...
...and please take care of Daddy
up in heaven.
You're such a special little girl, Cindy.
Good night, honey.
If Eve 6 is right and there are
two other Eves out there...
...that could account for the two identical
murders occurring at exactly the same time.
Sally Kendrick does have
an accomplice - herself.
Until I heard that,
I'd begun to suspect the girls.
No, it seems the two remaining Eves
are doing away with the parents...
...in order to keep Tina and Cindy
in the family.
Do you suppose the girls have
any idea of what they are?
I hope not.
Let's go!
I'll take the back!
There's someone upstairs. Wait outside!
FBI! I'm armed!
Which one are you - Eve 7 or Eve 8?
Drop it.
You know I'm capable.
Slow.
Very slow.
The suspect's name is Sally Kendrick.
Early 40s, five foot eight, 135 pounds.
She may have an accomplice
similar in appearance.
Kendrick is driving a light-blue '93 Corolla.
She has exceptional strength for her size...
...so consider her armed and dangerous.
Quite possibly she'll display
severe psychotic behaviour.
The Oakland Bureau will orchestrate
the search across the bridge.
What if... What if she kills her?
First Doug, now Cindy.
The fact that Kendrick and her accomplice
just abducted the girls...
...tells us they want them alive.
I'm sure Cindy's alive and we'll find her.
And then what do we do?
I'm sorry you have to meet this way...
...but it's the best for all concerned.
Tina Simmons...
...meet Cindy Reardon.
Agent Scully?
They found the Corolla in the parking lot
of San Francisco International.
Start a check on
every single passenger list...
...for every flight that left
in the past 12 hours.
Check every terminal, make sure
she's not hiding out for a later flight.
Remember, she may have an accomplice.
A motel in Port Reyes has a guest
matching Sally's description.
- The car's at the airport.
- She might've ditched it.
The manager says
she checked in with a girl.
She left the hotel in the afternoon alone,
then returns with the girl.
Someone else could've picked her up
without him knowing.
The area is full of families.
There are hundreds of kids around.
This kid told him to use chlorine...
...to eradicate the dinoflagellates
in the swimming pool.
- Does that sound like someone you know?
- That's it.
I've always kept a close eye
on your behaviour, no matter where I was.
The last few years I spent
in search of the remaining Eve.
That, however, was cut short
by your... "activity".
I hoped my work at the Stapes Center
had corrected the Litchfield flaws.
Psychotic behaviour didn't develop
in the Adams and Eves until age 16.
Homicidal behaviour at 20.
Imagine my... disappointment...
...when I learned of
your accelerated development.
How did you learn
of each other's existence?
We just knew.
Did you discuss...
...how you would orchestrate
your little... prank?
We just knew.
Why murder your fathers?
- They weren't our fathers.
- We have no parents.
We weren't born.
We were created.
You...
You cannot think that way.
You're human beings.
Different, special...
...but you cannot give in to genetic destiny.
That's why I've taken you.
I was raised by a man who knew what I was.
He was a genetic engineer on the project.
With the proper environment...
...and a programme...
of long-term medication...
...you can become like me...
...and...
...not the other Eves.
Wh-What have you done?
Your soda...
...four ounces of foxglove.
Extracted...
...from a digitalis plant...
...this much is a lethal dose.
We cultivated them ourselves.
Wh-Why?
- You tell us.
- You made us.
We're your mistake.
I'll...
...c-correct... that mistake!
Well, I waited like you told me.
No-one's come in or out.
Get the back!
We were all supposed to drink,
but we only pretended to drink it.
They tried to poison us.
Who's "they"?
She and another lady.
What did the other lady look like?
Eve 8.
They were working together.
It's all right, we'll take care of you.
You're safe with us.
Looks like the Eves mixed
about four ounces of digitalis in each glass.
Their own mini-Jonestown.
Eve 6 said they were prone to suicide.
It has a sweet flavour, probably
not even perceptible in soda.
We're searching the area, but so far
there's no sign of the other suspect.
An officer'll take the girls back.
Maybe it'd be best if we take
responsibility for the girls.
We can get them checked out by a doctor.
OK, whatever.
Come on, girls, we're gonna take you back.
- Back where?
- What's gonna happen to Tina?
We'll talk about it in the car, OK?
They've already grown so attached.
It's gonna be hard
when Tina's placed in care.
Yeah.
Agent Mulder, I have to go to the bathroom.
Me, too.
- Can you hold it?
- I really need to go.
I could use some caffeine.
Hi.
- Where's your bathroom?
- In the back. You'll need a key.
Thanks.
- Oh, can I get four diet sodas?
-  Regular.
All right, uh, two diet
and two regular to go, please.
Thanks.
Agent Scully, my door's stuck.
Just a second.
Just a minute.
It's OK, my dad will pay for them
when he gets out of the bathroom.
OK.
- Those are the diet?
- I think these are.
Are you sure? It's really sweet.
- Try it.
- I know it's diet. I saw her pour it.
- OK.
-  Let's go.
Come on.
- Don't forget the drinks.
- Right.
- How much?
- $5.
- Wanna pay?
- Sure.
There you go.
You got those?
Thanks.
Tastes syrupy.
Cindy, did you pick up my keys
off the counter?
No.
No? All right, I'll be right back.
- Scully!
- What?
Scully...
Just wanted to open the car door for you.
Mulder!
It's them. They poisoned it.
Let's just get them in the car.
I only had a sip.
We didn't drink enough to make us sick.
Scully, I got 'em!
- Leave us alone!
- I got 'em!
Scully!
Hey!
- What the hell are you doing?
- I'm a federal agent!
Yeah, and these
are America's Most Wanted?
- Hands in front.
- Leave me alone!
- Let the girls go!
- Get in the truck, girls. Get in.
- I'm gonna call the police.
- We are the police!
Mulder!
They went that way!
You seen the twins we were with?
No, I...
There's a bunch of schoolkids
just left on that bus.
Forget your sodas?
- We didn't do anything wrong.
- We're just little girls.
That's the last thing you are.
They said they have an excellent
programme that can help her.
They can't hide behind a bureaucracy,
Mrs Reardon.
You have a right to know what happened,
a right to know about your daughter.
All I need to know is
she was not my daughter.
She never was.
Hello, girls.
It's so nice to have company.
Sign for this.
Hello, Eve 8.
We've been waiting.
How did you know I'd come for you?
- We just knew.
Pam Atkinson
I made this!