Eugene?
Eugene, it's Dr Monte.
Eugene, are you asleep?
No.
I was on my way out.
I wanted to stop by and see
how you were feeling.
Fine.
Good.
You nervous about tomorrow?
Don't be.
I know you think they won't let you out,
so I peeked at the reports...
...of the doctors that will
testify at your review.
They concur with my opinion
that you're ready to be released...
Mm.
...and rejoin the community.
So...
...why don't we get some sleep and relax...
...and I'll see you tomorrow
at the review, OK?
Let's just keep our fingers crossed.
Agent Scully...
...we have reviewed your reports
and frankly we are displeased.
Irregular procedure, untenable evidence...
...anonymous witnesses, inconclusive
findings aggravated by vague opinion.
The nature of X-Files cases often
precludes orthodox investigation.
Do you suggest we adopt separate
standards for you and Mulder?
No.
Does Agent Mulder obstruct you
from proper procedure?
No, sir. I'm suggesting these cases
be reviewed with an open mind.
Maybe your mind has become too open.
On cases investigated
by Mulder and myself to date...
...we have a conviction
or case solution of 75%...
...well above Bureau standard.
That is your only saving grace.
May I ask, sir, what more you require?
What I require is
increased frequency of reports...
...conventional investigation.
In short, Agent Scully,
it is your responsibility...
...to see that these cases are by the book.
I understand. However...
...conventional investigation
of these cases...
...may decrease the rate of success.
By order...
...of the State of Maryland,
the court shall review...
...the psychological status
of Eugene Victor Tooms.
We'll begin with
the court-appointed expert witnesses.
The court calls...
...Dr Pamela Karetzky.
I performed several diagnostic
procedures on Mr Tooms...
...in order to determine any organic
physiological dysfunction.
An electroencephalogram...
...chromosomal analysis,
a computerised axial tomograph.
All of these were negative.
"Mr Tooms had recently lost his job...
"Aggravated by a false arrest by the FBI...
...his assault on Agent Scully was...
...'frustration directed at the wrong person'."
I am reading from a recent interview
I did with Mr Tooms...
...at the Druid Hill Sanitarium.
If you were released,
what is the first thing you would do?
- I'd like my old job back.
- Why?
The animal shelter made me
feel I was helping everyone...
...people and animals.
Mr Tooms has learned
to articulate his feelings...
...and invest his emotional energy
and creative energy in...
...stratagems he can build up in himself.
It is my opinion that Mr Tooms...
...has had an excellent response
to the treatment and therapy.
I would see no reason
why he would be any danger...
...to himself or any member of society.
Do you swear your testimony is the truth,
the whole truth and nothing but the truth?
I do.
Mr Mulder, as an expert witness
for the State of Maryland...
...can you list your qualifications?
I'm a special agent with the FBI.
I worked for three years
at its behavioural science unit...
...profiling serial killers.
Your Honour,
I know where he's going with this.
Mr Tooms was placed in psychiatric care...
...solely for the assault on Agent Scully.
He has never been charged
with any other crime.
You may proceed... with caution.
Agent Mulder, I understand...
...you've drawn on your experience
to profile Mr Tooms.
- Yes, I have.
- Please.
These murders span nearly a century.
19 homicides, five occurring
every 30 years since 1903.
All in the Baltimore area.
In each case, the liver was extracted...
...and presumably eaten.
A trophy was taken from each victim,
many of which were found...
...in the living quarters
of Eugene Tooms at 66 Exeter Street.
Records show that a Eugene Tooms has
resided at that same address since 1903...
...the same year a man
was murdered in that building.
Besides liver extraction...
...the most notable link
is the undetermined point of entry.
Many victims were found with their
windows and doors locked from the inside.
These elongated fingerprints
found at 7 of the 19 crime scenes...
...match Tooms.
Agent Mulder, look at his fingers.
- Look at him.
- Perhaps through a genetic mutation...
...Eugene Tooms is capable
of elongating his body...
...to access victims
so he may extract the livers...
...which provide sustenance for
the hibernation period of 30 years.
- He needs one more victim.
- Your Honour!
An exam done at the time of his arrest...
...revealed muscle and bone abnormalities.
- His attorney blocked further study.
- Thank you!
- Counsel?
- No further questions, Your Honour.
- This an abnormal human creature.
- Agent Mulder!
You may step down.
If you release Tooms, he will kill again.
It's in his genetic make-up.
Think they'd have taken me more seriously
if I wore the grey suit?
Mulder, your testimony, you sounded so...
I don't care as long as it was the truth.
Where were you?
- Your testimony was important.
- I was called into a meeting.
- By Assistant Director Skinner.
- What did he want?
He just wanted to reel me in.
They're ready.
It is the opinion of this court...
...that Eugene Victor Tooms...
...shall on this day be released
from the Druid Hill Sanitarium.
The court also attaches these conditions.
One...
...that he remain in counselling
under the care of Dr Aaron Monte...
...that he retain his job at Baltimore
Animal Shelter, and last...
...that he take residence in the house of
Mr and Mrs Arlan Green, trained...
...to assist patients from Druid Hill
in their transition to society.
Mr Tooms...
...do you understand and accept
these conditions?
Yes, Your Honour.
Very well. You're free to go.
- I'm not taking my eyes off him.
- Mulder...
He'll kill the first chance he can,
but he won't kill the old couple.
Tooms didn't remain a secret
for 100 years by not being careful.
He'll only kill out of necessity
or self-defence.
If he makes an attempt, I'll stop him.
I'll keep surveillance with you.
I'll watch him. Go back to the earlier
murders to prove it was him.
- That was 30 or 60 years ago.
- Murder has no statute of limitation.
Mulder, that's going to entail
unorthodox methods of investigation.
If you're resistant because
you don't believe, I'll respect that.
If it's because of bureaucratic pressure...
...they've reeled you in and skinned you.
I hope you'll
be comfortable, Eugene.
The room in the back is small...
..but I'm sure you'll be able to squeeze in.
I'm sure.
Excuse me...
could you help me find my dog?
He's a Norwegian elkhound.
His name is Heinrich.
I use him to hunt moose.
If Tooms gets away now...
...then the next time he takes a life...
...you'll be nearly my age.
Detective Briggs,
you helped us so much before.
Now we have to prove that Tooms
was involved in the killings...
...you investigated 30 years ago.
You've lived with this case...
...half your life.
There must be something... maybe
a connection between the victims.
I know we've seen all the evidence...
...but is there anything, anything at all...
...amongst the evidence that does not fit?
There was something...
...that never did sit quite right with me.
All of the victims that I investigated in '63...
...were found at the crime scene,
liver extracted - all five.
As were the four most recent murders.
When I was a sheriff...
...during the Pohattan Mills
killings of 1933...
...only four of the victims
were found at the crime scene.
However, there was a fifth person...
...who was missing and never found.
But this...
This was discovered
at the Ruxton chemical plant...
...when it was under construction.
It doesn't belong to the other victims.
That doesn't prove it belongs to
a person murdered by Tooms.
I'm positive Tooms hid this one victim...
...because something about the body
could prove he was the killer.
- What makes you positive?
- A hunch. An old-fashioned hunch.
You've got to trust your instincts.
And... what does your instinct say
about where Tooms buried the body?
In the cement
where they poured the foundation...
...of the chemical plant.
Ground-penetrating radar.
It bounces signals off objects or cavities.
Tells you where the body is.
Well, it signals if something
inordinate is present.
An experienced operator
attempts to differentiate...
...if a signal is a body or a stone
or a hole in the ground.
- Differentiates?
- Mm-hm.
You mean he guesses.
Well, it's an educated guess.
Mm-hm.
How are we doing?
Well, it's really hard to tell.
There are some possibilities.
Nothing very conclusive...
It's here!
Here!
What is it?
It's here!
Right here!
Agent Scully, look at this.
Robo-toddler's finally sleeping!
I'm gonna watch TV in bed.
OK.
I'm coming, honey.
Oh, screw it!
Would you go down and get that?
FBI.
I suspect an intruder in your house.
What?
Someone opened my window!
I suspect the year of death
to be in the mid-1930s.
The anterior surface...
...of the right femur was green,
indicating exposure to copper.
We concentrated on the area
and we found several pennies.
1933... '31... 1933.
Can you determine cause of death?
My instinct says burial in cement is murder.
No, at the moment I have found
no definite proof of murder.
There are gnawing marks near the ribs.
I suspect that's rodent activity...
...prior to the body being set in cement.
We need to see more of the remains
for cause of death.
As you know, it's a slow
but necessary process.
I did try a little something.
It's a little premature
if we're gonna go by the book.
Well, we'll keep it off the record.
Good. Thank you.
The old man, Mr Briggs...
...gave me a photograph
of the missing person in 1933...
...suspected of being a murder victim.
I ran a computer-aided superimposition
on what we have of the skull.
Now... this is not official...
...but that skeleton was that person.
It's not enough. It doesn't tie it to Tooms.
Well, it's a start.
Mulder, it's getting a bit ripe
in here, don't you think?
Pine-scented!
Ohh!
Better?
Tooms hasn't come out of the house all day.
I've sat through a Phillies game
and four hours of Baba Booey.
When it got dark, I took a walk.
Got that sandwich I asked for?
Mm.
It's liverwurst.
You know proper surveillance
requires two pairs of agents...
...one pair relieving the other after 12 hours.
Article 30, paragraph 8.7?
This isn't about doing it by the book.
You haven't slept for three days.
You're gonna get sloppy and
you're gonna get hurt. It's inevitable.
A request for other agents
to stake out Tooms would be denied.
Then I'll stay, you go home.
They're out to put an end
to the X-Files, Scully.
I don't know why, but any excuse will do.
I don't really care about my record...
...but you'd be in trouble
just sitting in this car.
I'd hate to see you carry an official
reprimand in your file because of me.
Fox...
I... I... even made my parents
call me Mulder.
Mulder.
Mulder, I wouldn't put myself
on the line for anybody but you.
If there's an iced tea in that bag...
...it could be love.
Must be fate, Mulder.
Root beer.
You're delirious.
Go home and get some sleep.
Take my sandwich. I only had one bite.
You're gonna want it later.
Call me if anything happens.
Immediately. I'll be here.
Oh, oh, and 11.30, station 790...
...Pete Rose's late-night
sports talk radio show.
I wouldn't miss it for the world
It has worked, hasn't it?
You'll be all right now.
I know it's worked!
Yeah, they found him out cold in the street.
He's been beaten up pretty badly.
Contusions, multiple lacerations.
The shoulder's been pulled right out of joint.
Let's get him prepped
for some blood work and X-rays.
He's been kicked in the jaw.
It may be fractured.
There's a partial shoe print.
I wanna get a photo of that.
We might be able to find
the shoe that matches it later.
Do you know who did this to you?
We'll be right back, Mr Tooms.
Says it was
an FBI agent named Mulder.
So would you say he's delusional
or just schizophrenic?
It's just a cursory exam,
but there's nothing to indicate that.
- Agent Mulder?
- Yeah.
What's going on?
What's this about?
Agent Mulder, get your things.
You're in some trouble.
These are serious allegations.
The evidence is incriminating.
A good forensic scientist would know
there is not only a shoe print...
...but an impact point of the foot
from inside the shoe.
An analysis of Tooms's injury would show...
...my foot was not inside the shoe.
Are you suggesting Tooms is framing you?
- Of course.
- If you had him under surveillance...
...how could he gain access
to your shoe without you seeing him?
- Well...
- Sir.
I was engaged in the unauthorised
surveillance as well.
Agent Mulder was orienting me...
...on the situation at the time
Tooms was admitted into the hospital.
Agent Mulder could not have done it
because he was with me.
Agent Scully, you wouldn't be
lying to me, would you?
Sir, I would expect you to place
the same trust in me as I do in you.
Agent Scully, may I have a word
with Agent Mulder, please?
Fox...
...you were one of the finest,
most unique agents...
...in the nearly 60-year history
of this institution.
We were talking about you
when you were in the academy.
Most of us, including the director,
feel you are wasted on the X-Files.
But we respect that you are
deeply invested in those areas.
But if these cases are creating such stress...
...as to cause not only you
to act inappropriately...
...but agents close to you...
...then may I advise you to step away...
...for a while?
Clear your head, take an extended vacation.
That's a good idea.
Thanks for your concern.
You're forbidden to go near Eugene Tooms.
Mulder...
...this was close.
Any closer and 1,000 friends at the
Capitol won't be able to help you.
These are Eugene Tooms's dental X-rays...
...obtained from the Druid Hill Sanitarium.
Your sandwich the other night
gave me an idea.
Dr Plith had mentioned that he found
gnawing on the rib cage...
...near the location of the liver.
Further excavation revealed...
...more pronounced bite marks,
human teeth marks.
Tooms will never voluntarily
submit to a dental cast.
This software can create
a three-dimensional model...
...of Tooms's mouth
from the dental radiograph.
We've also mapped out the bite marks
from the skeleton's rib - here.
They match.
Eugene, Dr Monte.
Hi, I wanted to stop by and see
how everything was going.
Susan and I are going out for the evening.
- See you later.
- Thanks.
Great place.
Wonderful place. How are you feeling?
Why the newspaper strips, Eugene?
Are you making some papier-mâché?
Yes.
That's terrific, wonderful.
I had no idea you were interested in art.
I like art.
I do, too. I'm very proud of you.
Art can provide a window...
...to your thoughts and your feelings.
What are you doing, Eugene?
Eugene... are you all right?
Arghhhh!
That makes five.
He's building his nest.
- 30-year hibernation.
- Where would he go?
Where he's gone for the last 90 years -
66 Exeter Street.
No, I already checked.
They tore down that apartment building.
What's there now?
Thanks.
He's gotta be here.
If he's drawn to this location
for some reason...
...maybe this nest is in the approximate
location of the previous nest.
This is the area.
There's a storage facility...
...on the second floor.
What?
There's only room for one.
You can get the next mutant.
Mulder?
Mulder! Mulder, here!
Quick, grab my hand!
- Come on!
- Mulder, what's happening?
Quick!
Have you read this report?
Do you believe them?
Of course I do.
OK, let's go.
It's amazing how things change, isn't it?
The caterpillar?
No, a change for us.
- It's coming.
- How do you know?
A hunch.
Subtitles by Visiontext
I made this!