♪♪
I KNOW A LOT OF DIVERS HAVE BEEN
KILLED 15, 10 FEET OF WATER.
AND I NEED THE FEAR
TO GIVE ME -- TO CAUTION.
LET'S GET
SOME HOT WATER GOING.
IT'S GETTING WARM.
IT AIN'T HOT YET.
READY TO ROCK AND ROLL, BRO?
ROCK AND ROLL!
YOU GUYS GOT ME, RIGHT?!
YOU GOT ME? YOU GOT ME?
YEP. WE GOT YOU, BUDDY.THAT'S ALL I NEED, MAN.
♪♪
OHH, YEAH!
Man: UH,
ARE YOU GETTING COLD?
I'M GONNA
REV UP THE ENGINE.
ALL RIGHT, WE MAXED OUT
THE ENGINES JUST NOW.
-GET HIM OUT OF THERE!
-YOU GOT BURNED.
OH, MY [BLEEP]
♪♪
THINK YOU PUT ON
A LITTLE WEIGHT, BUDDY.
SUCK IT UP.
HERE WE GO, BUDDY!
MOMENT OF TRUTH.
♪♪
WHOA! WHOA! WHOA! WHOA!
STOP! STOP! STOP! STOP!
HI, I'M DUSTIN.
DUSTIN, I'M CASEY.THIS IS MY CAMP.
I WILL GET YOU TO THE BOTTOM
OF THAT HOLE
AND FIND THAT GOLD
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR.
I'LLGET ME
DOWN TO THAT HOLE.
♪♪
I'VE GOT $75,000 INTO THIS,
AND I NEED ABOUT 60 OUNCES
TO BREAK EVEN RIGHT NOW.
TODAY, WE'RE GONNA PUT IN
TWO DREDGES.
FRED'S GONNA BE ON ONE.
I'M GONNA BE ON THE OTHER ONE.
WITH ANY LUCK, WE'RE GONNA BE
ABLE TO DIG THIS HOLE
IN ABOUT TWO WEEKS.
I KNOW THERE'S GOLD DOWN THERE.
WE'RE GONNA GET TO IT THIS YEAR.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
Narrator: HIGH IN ALASKA'S
CHILKAT MOUNTAINS,
THE DAKOTA BOYS ARE DIVING
FOR MILLIONS OF DOLLARS OF GOLD
BURIED ON THE BEDROCK BENEATH
THE RAGING McKINLEY CREEK.
TO GET DOWN TO THE GOLD FASTER,
FATHER AND SON ARE DIVING
WITH TWO DREDGES.
♪♪
SO...
THIS WAS 15 FEET
IN THE LAST SEASON.
♪♪
AND NOW IT'S ONLY THREE
OR FOUR FEET.
YOU REALIZE WE GOT TO BE
TO THE TOP OF THAT POLE?
SO, RIGHT THERE.RIGHT THERE.
WE WERE SITTING AT 15 FEET.
IT'S 3 FEET DEEP RIGHT NOW.
HERE'S THE DEAL.
I NEED THIS HOLE TO BE DUG
AS FAST AS POSSIBLE
BEFORE THE FLOODS COME.
THERE'S A WHOLE BUNCH
OF GOLD DOWN THERE,
AND IT'S ON THE BEDROCK.
I WANT TO
GET DOWN TO THE GOLD.
Narrator: AT THE END OF LAST
SEASON, AFTER DIGGING 15 FEET,
THEY HIT A PILE OF GOLD
ON BEDROCK.
BUT BEFORE THEY COULD
GET IT OUT,
A FLASH FLOOD FILLED IN THEIR
HOLE WITH GRAVEL AND ROCKS.
OUR MAIN OBJECTIVE IS
TO GET DOWN TO THE GOLD.
IF WE PUT TWO DREDGES ON IT,
TWO DIVERS ON IT,
WE'RE OBVIOUSLY GONNA GET DOWN
TO THAT GOLD MUCH QUICKER.
TODAY IS
A BIG DAY FOR FRED.
WE'RE GONNA SET HIS DREDGE
IN THE WATER.
HE'S GONNA TRY TO GET THIS THING
IN WITHOUT LOSING IT.
Narrator:
LAST WEEK, THEY STARTED MINING
WITH DUSTIN'S BRAND-NEW DREDGE.
THIS WEEK,
THEY'RE DOUBLING DOWN
BY LAUNCHING
FRED'S OLD FAITHFUL.
Fred: WELL, WE'RE JUST USING
THIS ONE THAT WE ALREADY HAD.
WE GOT A NICE, LITTLE
SIX-INCH DREDGE HERE.
THIS IS A VERY
SOPHISTICATED MACHINE.
IT'S GOT AIR.
IT'S GOT HOT WATER.
♪♪
I'VE GOT TO SET UP
THIS WINCH SYSTEM
SO FRED CAN GET HIS DREDGE
OUT HERE.
♪♪
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
WE'RE TESTING
THIS [BLEEP] DANG
WINCH SYSTEM.
Wes: YEAH, IT IS.
WELL, IF THEY DON'T HAUL
THIS DREDGE, WE'RE IN TROUBLE.
Narrator: FIRST, DUSTIN NEEDS
TO RETRIEVE THE HOOK THEY'LL USE
TO LIFT FRED'S DREDGE
INTO THE CREEK.
Wes: HEY, WE'VE GOT
AN ISSUE, MAN.
WHAT?
I'M NOT FAMILIAR
WITH THIS WINCH YET.
DON'T GET ME HURT.
WATCH THEM.
IF THAT STARTS GETTING TIGHT,
SLOW UP.
OKAY, WAIT. STOP.
STOP RIGHT THERE.
STOP!
WHOA! WHOA! WHOA! WHOA!
WHOA! WHOA!
STOP! STOP! STOP! STOP!
YOU CRAZY [BLEEP] YOU.
I GOT MY HAND CAUGHT.
I CAN'T --
AAH! WHY WOULD YOU DO
SUCH A THING?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
HE CAUGHT HIMSELF --
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT'S GOING ON.
LUCKILY, WE STOPPED IT JUST
BEFORE HE PULLED HIS HAND OFF.
YOU GUYS [BLEEP] COMMUNICATE,
ALL RIGHT?
OH [BLEEP] JUST ABOUT
RIPPED ME UP, MAN.
WELL, WHAT ARE
WE ACCOMPLISHING HERE?
YOU GONNA COME DOWN?
YOU NEED MORE WEIGHT?
I'M GONNA
DROP IT DOWN FIRST.
♪♪
PERFECT.
NOW WE WON'T LOSE IT.
OH, MAN, THAT'S MORE
THAN ENOUGH.
ALL RIGHT, I'M DONE
WITH THIS [BLEEP]
♪♪
WE GOT TO GET
FRED'S DREDGE OUT OF HERE.
YOU WANT TO TAKE CONTROL
OF THIS,
OR YOU WANT ME
TO DO IT?
OKAY, WELL, WE NEED SIX PEOPLE
TO GET IT OUT THERE, THEN.
YOU HAVE TO
BE IN CONTROL.
YOU CAN'T BE YELLING
AND [BLEEP]
GOOD COMMUNICATIONS,
OLD MAN.
[ LAUGHS ]
-WE'RE SLIDING?
-SLIDE.
SLOW. SLOW. SLOW.
EVERYBODY SLOW DOWN.
ALL RIGHT.
♪♪
-JUST WATCH THAT SYSTEM!
-OH.
Fred: GO AHEAD.
COMING UP.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE COMING UP
A LITTLE BIT.
HEY, ANYBODY GOT A HOLD
OF THE OTHER LINE?
ALL RIGHT.
GET YOUR OTHER LINE.
WHAT THE HELL ARE Y'ALL
DOING UP THERE?
I-I DON'T LIKE THE SYSTEM
BECAUSE IT RELIES
ON THE COORDINATION BETWEEN
THIS WINCH AND THAT WINCH.
Narrator: THE BLUE WINCH
LIFTS THE DREDGE OFF THE BRIDGE.
THE RED WINCH MOVES IT
HORIZONTALLY ABOVE THE CREEK.
DUSTIN HAS TO SYNCHRONIZE
THE TWO WINCHES PERFECTLY.
PERFECT.
OH, YEAH!
HEY! YO!
YOU WANT TO TWIST IT?
WE'RE GONNA SPIN IT.TAKE IT ALL THE WAY UP.
TWIST IT AROUND.TWIST IT AROUND.
THERE YOU GO.
PASS IT ON OVER HERE.
ALL RIGHT!
HEADS UP!
REAL SLOW, BUDDY!
OH! OH! OH! OH! OH!
WHOA!
STOP! STOP!
HOLD IT!
THAT'S WHAT
I DON'T LIKE.
[BLEEP] HAVE
ONE DIRECTOR.
JUST ONE DIRECTION
AT A TIME.
WELL, YOU GOT TO WATCH
WHAT'S ACTUALLY HAPPENING.
I'M WATCHING.
HE WAS IN THE WATER.
LET HER DOWN.
CHECK THE BRAKE.
OH, HE'S GOT IT
FIGURED OUT NOW.
ONE MORE TIME.
Fred: THERE YOU GO.
♪♪
Dustin: THERE IT GOES.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT!
GOT IT!
GOOD SHOW, MAN.
GOOD SHOW.
Y'ALL ACTUALLY
GOT IT IN THERE.
YOU LIKE MY SYSTEM YET?NO, I DON'T.
AW [BLEEP] MAN,
COME ON.
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU SERIOUS?
I MEAN, TO LAUNCH IT,
IT'S FINE.
BUT WE'LL SEE HOW THINGS GO
WITH THE ROCKS, OKAY?
LET'S GO WITH IT.
I'VE GOT SO MUCH TIME AND MONEY
TIED UP IN THIS
THAT I HAVE
TO GET THIS HOLE DUG.
AND WE'RE GONNA START
DIGGING TODAY.
TODAY'S DIG DAY.
Narrator:
THE DAKOTA BOYS FINALLY HAVE
TWO DREDGES IN McKINLEY CREEK.
DUSTIN'S DREDGE WILL MINE
ONE SIDE OF THE CREEK.
FRED'S WILL MINE THE OTHER.
I'M GONNA GET
IN THE WATER TODAY.
TODAY IS GONNA BE
MY FIRST DAY OF DIVING.
WE'RE GONNA SEE
IF WE CAN KICK A LITTLE ASS.
♪♪
ALWAYS SAID IF YOU CAN GET INTO
A WET SUIT, YOU CAN BE A DIVER.
[ LAUGHS ]MY GOODNESS.
I THINK YOU PUT ON
A LITTLE WEIGHT, BUDDY.
SUCK IT UP.
Narrator: FOR THE FIRST TIME,
74-YEAR-OLD FRED HURT
AND HIS SON DUSTIN ARE DIVING
TOGETHER IN THE RAGING WATERS.
FIRE 'EM UP!
♪♪
HEY, FRED.
YOU AND ME.
HERE WE GO, BUDDY.
MOMENT OF TRUTH.
TODAY'S THE DAY, FELLAS.
Got me on comms?
YOU'RE GOOD.
YEAH, YOU'RE GOOD.
LET ME PUT MY COMMS ON.
All right.
Whoo!
ALL RIGHT, FRED,
YOU'RE READY TO ROCK.
ALL RIGHT, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
DIVERS IN THE WATER.
Narrator: THE DIVERS ARE
CONNECTED TO THE DREDGE
BY AN UMBILICAL LIFELINE MADE UP
OF THREE CRUCIAL COMPONENTS.
TO STOP HIM BEING SWEPT AWAY,
THE DIVER HAS A SAFETY CORD
ATTACHED TO HIS HARNESS.
A HOSE CARRIES HOT WATER
FROM THE DREDGE
TO THE SUIT
TO AVOID HYPOTHERMIA.
THE THIRD LINE DELIVERS AIR
TO THE DIVER'S MASK.
A FAULT WITH ANY OF THESE
COULD BE FATAL.
Let me turn you up.
I got you cut down right now.
Are you ready for more?
Yeah.
Let's do it.
Okay, open her up.
Okay.
Whoo!
Welp, they're
dredging, too.
So, we got two dredges going.
That's a first.
FINALLY BACK TO WORK!
Narrator:
IN THESE EXTREME CONDITIONS,
FRED'S DREDGE
CAN RUN SIX YARDS AN HOUR...
DUSTIN'S, OVER 12.
THEY CAN RUN A FULL THREE TIMES
AS FAST AS THEY DID LAST SEASON.
Looks good
so far, Fred.
Narrator: UP AHEAD...
♪♪
Narrator: IN McKINLEY CREEK,
FRED AND DUSTIN HURT
ARE DIVING SIDE-BY-SIDE
FOR THE FIRST TIME
ON THE HUNT FOR BEDROCK GOLD.
Whoo!
PAUL IS RUNNING THE DREDGE
AND ON COMMS WITH DUSTIN.
PAUL:
Everything looks good right now.
AND CARLOS IS TENDING THE SAFETY
LINES TO DUSTIN'S DIVE SUIT.
RICH: Yeah!
GREENHORN RICH IS ON COMMS,
RUNNING THE DREDGE,
AND TENDING THE SAFETY LINES
FOR 74-YEAR-OLD FRED.
THEY'RE PUSHING THE HOT-WATER
RIGS TO THE LIMIT
IN THE 38-DEGREE CREEK.
Oh, wow.
PAUL: He hasn't come up yet,
so it looks pretty good for him.
Okay.
MY FEET GOT SO COLD,
I COULDN'T FEEL
THE BALANCE UNITS IN THEM.
SORT OF RESTRICTING
THE WATER FLOW DOWN TO MY FEET.
Dustin's out
of the water already.
OH, YEAH, I SEE
SOME DIRTY WATER COMING OUT.
YEAH, I'M JUST NOT SEEING
THE WATER
OUT OF THE SLUICE BOX
LIKE I SHOULD.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GONNA
GET OFF THE COMMS.
ALL RIGHT.
Narrator:
RICH PUTS DOWN THE DIVER'S COMMS
TO REMOVE THE BLOCKAGE
FROM THE DREDGE.
HOLD ON.
[BLEEP] GET THAT THING
OFF FROM ME!
WELL, THEN,
TAKE IT OFF, FRED.
I CAN'T DO EVERYTHING
AT ONCE, BUDDY.
♪♪
THAT'S IT, MAN.
WE AIN'T DOING NO MORE DIVING
TILL I GET ANOTHER
PAIR OF MEN OUT HERE.
I CANNOT RUN THE DREDGE,
TAKE CARE OF THE FUEL,
UNPLUG THE DREDGE,
RUN THE SLATS...
DEAL WITH THE UMBILICAL.
IT'S JUST TOO MUCH
FOR ONE PERSON
ON THE TOPSIDE TO DEAL WITH.
I NEED SOME HELP.
THAT'S IT.
IT AIN'T GONNA
BE HAPPENING NO MORE.
WE AIN'T GONNA DIVE
WITH JUST ONE PERSON ON TOP.
Fred: I NEED ANOTHER MAN
OUT HERE.
GOT TO.
THERE'S JUST NO --
I MEAN, I'M NOT GONNA EVEN BE
HERE IF I DON'T GET ANOTHER MAN.
OKAY.
THERE'S NO REASON
TO EVEN BE THERE.
I UNDERSTAND
YOU NEED SOME HELP.
WHY DON'T YOU GET
IN THAT HOT ROOM, MAN?
YEAH.
♪♪
CASEY. HEY,
HOW YOU DOING, MAN?
WHAT'S YOUR SITUATION RIGHT NOW?
CAN YOU COME UP LATER THIS WEEK?
ALL RIGHT.
YOU JUST MADE MY DAY.
[ CHUCKLES ]
♪♪
Narrator: CASEY MORGAN HAS OVER
10 YEARS EXPERIENCE GOLD MINING
AND DREDGING IN ARIZONA.
HI, I'M DUSTIN.
DUSTIN, I'M CASEY.THIS IS MY CAMP.
ALL RIGHT, JUST SO YOU KNOW,
THIS IS THE REAL DEAL.
THIS IS DANGEROUS.
WHAT IS IT YOU'VE DONE?
LIKE, WHAT KIND OF MINING
HAVE YOU DONE?
I'VE DONE JUST ABOUT EVERY TYPE
OF MINING THERE IS FOR GOLD.
DONE BLASTER MINING,
I'VE DONE A LITTLE BIT
OF LOAD MINING, DREDGING.
I WILL GET YOU
TO THE BOTTOM OF THAT HOLE
AND FIND THAT GOLD
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR.
I'LL GET ME
DOWN TO THAT HOLE.
ONE OF THE IMPORTANT THINGS
FOR ME IS YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
HAVE A POSITIVE ATTITUDE
ABOUT THIS.
SAYING THE WORDS,
"THIS IS A LOT OF WORK,"
"BUT WE CAN'T DO THIS,"
ALL THE TIME
IS GONNA GET YOU
SENT OUT OF HERE.
I'VE PUT PEOPLE OUT BEFORE
BECAUSE OF THAT.
WELCOME TO
THE MINE SITE.
STAY SAFE, AND LET'S
GET SOME WORK DONE, ALL RIGHT?
DO YOU HAVE
ANY QUESTIONS?
WHERE DO I GET
IN THE WATER?
♪♪
Fred: TODAY IT'S GONNA BE
A BAPTISM OF FIRE, MAN.
GONNA LET CASEY TRY HIS
FIRST DAY OF DIVING OUT HERE.
SEE IF IT'LL FIT.
YOU GOT TO STEP INTO IT, THOUGH.
STEP INTO IT? OH,
IT'S A SPRING SUIT. ALL RIGHT.
HE CAN'T WEAR MINE
'CAUSE HE'S TALLER THAN ME.
Fred: I WILL BE TENDING YOU
PERSONALLY.
I WILL NOT BE EVER
OFF THE COMMS.
YOU'RE TOO HOT, YOU'RE FLOODING
YOUR MASK, YOU'RE --
WHATEVER YOU'RE DOING, YOU YELL,
"HELP! HELP! HELP!"
THIS IS
WHAT I CAME TO DO --
HELP FRED GET THAT DAMN GOLD
OUT OF THE BOTTOM OF THIS RIVER.
THAT'S MY GOAL.
NEED TO GET ALL OF IT!
I WANT ALL THE GOLD!
Narrator:
EXPERIENCED MINER CASEY MORGAN
IS DIVING ON HIS FIRST DAY.
-Are you ready?
-READY?
ALL RIGHT.
♪♪
THERE YOU GO.
YOU GOT IT.
BIG, STRONG GUY,
LIKES THE WATER, LIKES THE WORK.
I THINK
HE'S HAVING A BLAST.
CASEY: [ Laughs ]
Oh, yeah. How's your water?
How's everything feeling?
What?
Hold on. Slow down.
Slow down. Slow down.
Catch your breath.
All right, I'll take them.
All right, there's a pick over
your head with a screwdriver.
All right.
Don't want
to drop them.
All right.
Diver's preference.
Well, he's gonna do
what he can to get it out,
so I'm gonna
have to trust him.
All right.
IT'S NOT GOLD.
[ LAUGHS ]
Damn it!
CASEY THOUGHT HE SAW SOME GOLD
STUCK IN A CRACK IN THE WALL.
THE FIRST ONE'S NOT IT.
Well...what did the other one
look like?
That's all right, man.
That's all right.
We'll teach you what the gold
looks like eventually.
[ Laughs ]
Diver coming up.
Oh, boy, that's a --
-GOOD JOB!
-WHOO!
Fred: CASEY HAD HIS FIRST DAY
IN THE WATER.
I KNOW WHERE THE HELL I'M GONNA
USE HIM A LOT THIS YEAR.
GOOD JOB, MAN.THANK YOU.
GOOD JOB.
I'VE SEEN GOLD A MILLION TIMES.
LOOKED LIKE GOLD.
LITTLE ROUND, NICE,
LITTLE NUGGETS.
I WAS WRONG.
GOT TO ADMIT -- PROUD OF HIM.
Dustin:
CASEY'S IN TRAINING RIGHT NOW.
YEAH, HE DOESN'T KNOW
WHAT THE [BLEEP] HE'S DOING.
♪♪
TIME TO GET STARTED
THIS MORNING.
FULL OF PISS AND VINEGAR.
ALL OF US ARE GONNA GO DOWN AND
FIND ME A WHOLE BUNCH OF GOLD.
♪♪
WE GOT 14 FEET TO --
WHAT YOU CALL IT -- DIG UP.
-SO THAT'S WHAT I'M DOING.
-ALL TODAY, MAN.
-YOU GETTING IT ALL.
-[ LAUGHS ]
Narrator: TODAY, FORMER MARINE
CARLOS MINOR IS STEPPING UP
FOR HIS FIRST DIVE
OF THE SEASON.
INTO THE WATER I GO,
BROTHER.
INTO THE GOLD I GET.
CONTACT.
GOOD LAUNCH, BROTHER!
GOOD LAUNCH!
♪♪
I'M READY TO GO ROCK AND ROLL,
BROTHER.
YOU GOT BOOTS,
YOU GOT GLOVES.
I GOT BOOTS,
GOT GLOVES.
YOU GOT -- OKAY.I'M READY TO ROCK AND ROLL.
ALL RIGHT, I GOT TO GO
TAKE CARE OF STUFF.
Narrator:
CARLOS HAS 15 YEARS EXPERIENCE
AS A COMMERCIAL DIVER,
BUT THIS IS HIS FIRST TIME
WITH DUSTIN'S NEW DREDGE.
Dustin: I WANT TO GET CARLOS IN
AND SEE WHAT HE CAN DO TODAY.
HE'S EXCITED TO GET IN.
I'M EXCITED TO HAVE HIM IN.
IT JUST -- TODAY'S THAT DAY.
LET'S GET
SOME HOT WATER GOING!
Rich: HOT WATER!
Narrator: DUSTIN WAS FORCED
TO ABANDON HIS LAST DIVE
IN THE FREEZING CREEK
WHEN THE HOT-WATER RIG FAILED.
THAT IS OUR WATER THAT'S COMING
OUT OF THE HEATER.
IT SEEMS
TO BE DOING THE TRICK.
Narrator: WES' HOMEMADE
HOT-WATER SYSTEM
PUMPS COLD CREEK WATER INTO
AN INSULATED CHAMBER
BUILT AROUND THE ENGINE
EXHAUST PIPE.
THE HOT EXHAUST HEATS
THE WATER AS IT RISES.
SCALDING WATER EXITS THE CHAMBER
AND IS MIXED WITH COLD CREEK
WATER BEFORE
IT'S FED TO THE DIVER.
♪♪
I LOVE TO GO COWBOY.
YOU HAVE TO GO COWBOY
IN ALASKA, MAN,
'CAUSE IT DOESN'T PLAY
BY YOUR RULES.
BUT TOO MUCH COWBOY IN HERE...
MAKES TROUBLE, MAN.
BAD MEDICINE IF YOU GET
TOO CRAZY HERE.
READY TO ROCK AND ROLL, BRO!
ROCK AND ROLL!
WHOO!
Dustin:
YOU GOT HIM, PAUL?
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET HIM
STRAIGHTENED OUT.
I'M COMING IN.
OH, MAN,
FEELING GOOD, DUDE.
♪♪
OH, HOT WATER.
WHOO, DOGGY!
YEAH!
YOU GUYS GOT ME, RIGHT?
YOU GOT ME. YOU GOT ME.
YOU GOT ME. GOOD.
WE GOT YOU, BUDDY.THAT'S ALL I NEED, MAN.
I'M FEELING
IN MY ELEMENT NOW, DUDE.
I'M TRYING TO GET TO 14 FEET,
MAN, WHERE WE GOT LAST TIME.
GREAT GOLD IS
UNDER THE 14 FEET.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
YOU WANT THE MASK
INSIDE OR OUTSIDE?
HUH?
IS THAT BETTER?Yeah.
Whoo!
Ohh, yeah!
Ohh [bleep]
Yeah, baby.
ARE YOU COMFORTABLE?
YOU ALL RIGHT?
LET'S PUT IN SOME TIME, MAN.
OH, YEAH.
DUDE, I FELT IT WAS PERFECT FOR
THAT CURRENT RIGHT THERE, MAN.
What's up?
Well, you'll find out.
We have first plug-up
if that's the case.
Nope, looks like everything's
coming through so far.
That's what I'm talking about,
man, right there.
YEAH!
Uh...
Okay, I'm gonna work
on the hot water a little bit.
All right, I moved it, so you
got to tell me how it goes.
It's a work in progress
right now, man.
Are you getting cold?
I'm gonna rev up
the engine a bit.
Sorry, I'm getting familiar
with this machine right now,
So you're gonna have to deal
with me for a little bit.
[ ENGINE REVVING INCREASES ]
I maxed it up.
All right, we maxed out
the engine just now.
OHH.
The water going out's
pretty damn warm right now.
Yeah, sorry for that.
Maybe --
You're not twisted?
You might want to pop up and see
if we can look at your lines
and see if you're twisted.
That's kind of my thoughts
on it right now.
Paul, can you pull these lines
to see what it looks like?
Let's get you
turned around, buddy.
So, we got to
take a look at you.
Yeah, you're kinked off.
You're kinked off, right?
So, you're gonna have to
come up to Paul.
Sorry, that's
what's going on.
I don't want to make this water
too hot.
If you're kinked off, it's gonna
burn the [bleep] out of you.
Yeah, you're kinked off
real bad, man. Sorry.
Narrator: CARLOS' HOSE HAS
FOLDED OVER ON ITSELF,
BLOCKING THE FLOW OF HOT WATER
TO HIS SUIT
IN THE FREEZING CREEK.
Paul, do I need to come up
with the water a little bit?
Yeah.
Okay, I see it.
It's a work in progress.
We'll get there.
I'm working on it.
Okay, you were kinked off.
I'm sorry.
We're gonna have to work
on the hose system.
Whoo!
Is it too hot?
All right,
open up your valve.
[BLEEP][ Screaming ]
Get it off! Get it off!
Get it off!
Undo him! Carlos!
GET HIM OUT OF THERE!
GET HIM OUT OF THERE! HURRY!
Get it off! Get it off!
Paul! Get it off!
Oh, my [BLEEP]
You got burned.
We burned you.
Oh, my [bleep]
[ Screaming ]
Get it off! Get it off!
Paul! Get it off!
Oh, my [BLEEP]
You got burned.
Oh, no.
Let's go check him out.
We got to go check him out.
♪♪
Narrator: CARLOS HAS BEEN BURNED
BY BOILING WATER
FROM A DREDGE MALFUNCTION.
Dustin: JUST RELAX.
JUST SLOW DOWN. SLOW DOWN.
EVERYBODY SLOW DOWN.
RIGHT NOW'S THE TIME
YOU NEED TO NOT PANIC.
ALL RIGHT, FRED.
♪♪
COME IN HERE?
Fred: WHO'S FIRST AID OUT HERE?
WHO IS FIRST AID?
I NEED A HALF A DOZEN
LITTLE PATCHES.
I AM THOROUGHLY TRAINED
IN ADVANCED FIRST AID.
CARLOS.Carlos: YEAH?
CAN I COME IN A MINUTE?YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
JUST ME.YOU CAN COME IN.
NOBODY ELSE.
HEY, LOOK.
OKAY, I GOT YOU.
WHAT ELSE?RIGHT THERE.
THIS IS YOUR WORST ONE
RIGHT HERE.
YEAH, A LITTLE BIT
OF LEG.
TELL YOU WHAT --
WRAP THAT UP THERE.
WE'LL JUST CATCH IT ALL THE WAY
RIGHT THERE.
BOY, THAT'S SOME BAD STUFF.
WE GOT TO GET HIM
TO THE HOSPITAL RIGHT AWAY,
GET HIM TREATED
FOR WHATEVER HE'S GOT THERE.
Dustin: HE SAID HE DIDN'T WANT
TO GO TO THE HOSPITAL.
HE'S GONNA HAVE TO GO.
HE HAS TO GO.
HE'S GOT A SECOND-DEGREE BURN
IN ABOUT FOUR PLACES.
HE HAS NO CHOICE,
BUT HE HAS TO GO.
GO AHEAD AND HEAD OUT.
DO SLOW. DON'T SWEAT A BUNCH.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
YOU AND I GOT
TO GET TO TOWN, MAN.
I'LL CARRY ALL YOUR STUFF.
GOT IT. I GOT IT.
♪♪
Narrator: THE MILE-LONG HIKE
TO THE CABLE CROSSING
IS THE FIRST PART
OF A PAINFUL TWO-HOUR JOURNEY
TO THE NEAREST DOCTOR
OVER 30 MILES AWAY.
♪♪
SECOND-DEGREE BURNS.
A COUPLE DAYS BED REST --
THREE DAYS BED REST --
THREE TO FIVE DAYS BED REST
AND TRY TO KEEP IT CLEAN.
TRY TO KEEP
THE INFECTION AWAY.
NO INFECTION
DOWN HERE IN ALASKA.
BAD MEDICINE.
♪♪
HEY, HOW'S CARLOS DOING?
HE LOST 1.5%
OF HIS SKIN.
YOUR FIST IS 1% PART
OF YOUR SKIN.
HE HAD A FIST AND A HALF
OF SKIN MISSING.
SO, HE'LL BE HEALING
FOR A WHILE.
I PUT HIM IN TOWN.
I THINK WHAT HAPPENED
IS I BURNED HIM MORE
BY FLIPPING THAT LEVER
THE WRONG WAY.
I THINK I GAVE HIM
TOO MUCH WATER.
INSTEAD OF CAPPING IT OFF,
I THINK I WENT THE WRONG WAY.
SO, I FEEL PERSONALLY
RESPONSIBLE FOR ALL OF THIS.
I JUST ABOUT WANTED
TO SHUT THIS DOWN YESTERDAY.
SO WE ALL NEED TO KNOW
WHERE I'M AT IN MY HEAD
'CAUSE WE CAN'T HAVE
THIS AGAIN.
NOBODY CAN
GET HURT AGAIN.
WE UNDERSTAND THE PROBLEM NOW.
NOW WE HAVE TO FIX IT.
THIS IS
A HUGE WAKE-UP CALL.
LET'S, UH...
LET'S DO BETTER, HUH?
WE GOT BROAD SHOULDERS,
TOO, MAN.
YEAH.
♪♪
DOWN.
DOWN, DOWN, DOWN.
I KNOW, MAN.
I'M NOT GOOD COMPANY RIGHT NOW.
I GOT TO WALK MY DOG,
SO, THAT'S...
BUT DOCTOR SAID IT COULD
HAVE BEEN A LOT WORSE.
I GUESS SHE KNEW
WHAT HOT-WATER SUITS WERE,
AND SHE SAID IT COULD HAVE
BEEN A LOT WORSE.
THIS IS ABOUT -- RIGHT HERE,
THE WAY I AM RIGHT NOW
IS THE ABOUT THE MOST
COMFORTABLE I CAN GET.
YOU THINK THAT LOOKS PRETTY BAD?
ALL THIS TIME I WORK
WITH THE HOT-WATER SUITS,
I JUST PUT IT ON,
AND I JUST TRUST THE FACT
THAT I'M GETTING HOT WATER.
NOW I KNOW WHERE
THEY ACTUALLY EXIT, YOU KNOW?
THIS IS MY BACK HERE.
I GOT ONE BACK HERE, WHICH ONE'S
A MENACE
BECAUSE THAT MEANS I GOT
TO HAVE MY PANTS SAGGING.
AND THEN EACH BACK ARM.
THAT PAIN WAS
SO UNDESCRIBABLE HOT.
ALL I WANTED TO DO
WAS OPEN MY SUIT
AND JUST GET
THE COLD WATER INSIDE.
THAT'S THE ONLY THING
I COULD THINK ABOUT, LITERALLY.
I HAD WHITE LIGHT JUST SHOOTING
THROUGH MY WHOLE BODY,
AND I COULDN'T CONCENTRATE.
IT WAS A CRAWFISH BOIL, MAN.
THAT'S HOW I FELT LIKE.
I'LL NEVER EAT ANOTHER CRAWFISH
WITHOUT FEELING SORRY
FOR THE [BLEEP]
♪♪
TODAY WE ARE HERE
NOT TO DIVE,
BUT TO MAKE SURE THAT NOT
ANOTHER PERSON GETS HURT HERE.
BEFORE SOMEBODY ELSE GETS
IN THAT WATER,
WE WILL HAVE THIS
SO LOCKED DOWN
IT WILL BE IMPOSSIBLE
FOR ANYONE TO GET BURNED.
♪♪
Narrator: WES IS UPGRADING
DUSTIN'S HOT-WATER SYSTEM.
LUCKILY, I SCROUNGED THIS
OVER THE WEEKEND --
AN OLD OXYGEN TANK, BUT IT'S
GONNA BE OUR NEW MIXING TANK.
SEE IF WE CAN MAKE
THIS BULLETPROOF.
SO, YOU GOT YOUR
ADJUSTMENT HERE.
COLD WATER COMING IN.
HOT WATER COMES INTO THIS.
SO IT'S GONNA MAKE
THE HOT-WATER RESERVOIR.
AND THEN
HOT WATER FEEDS THAT.
SO IF WE HAVE AN ISSUE WITH
A DIVER, THIS WILL SHUT OFF.
THAT SHUTS THE WATER OFF
TO THE DIVER,
AND THEN WE CAN HIT THAT
AND DUMP THE HOT WATER
IF WE NEED TO.
Narrator:
PAUL HAS COME UP WITH A SOLUTION
TO THE KINKING PROBLEM.
THIS IS THE HOSE RIGHT HERE THAT
CONNECTS TO OUR HOT-WATER UNIT.
NOW I'VE GOT SPRINGS
ALL THE WAY DOWN
TO WHERE IT CONNECTS
TO THE SUIT.
SO, THERE SHOULD BE NO ISSUE.
WITH THAT SPRING ON THERE,
THAT HOSE CANNOT KINK OFF.
IT'LL COIL UP, BUT IT WILL
NOT COLLAPSE ON ITSELF.
EVERY PART OF IT --
EVERYTHING --
YOU'RE GONNA TURN IT UP,
YOU'RE GONNA TURN IT DOWN,
VALVES ON, VALVES OFF, EMERGENCY
SHUT-OFF HOT WATER -- ALL OF IT.
EVERYBODY -- EVERYONE IS
GOING TO DO THIS.
EMERGENCY FIRE DRILLS.
THAT'S ALL WE GOT TO HAVE.
I KNOW THERE'S
A LOT OF GOLD DOWN THERE,
BUT AT THE COST
OF WHAT, MAN?
WE HAVE TO BE SAFE.
♪♪
Narrator: WES AND PAUL FIT
THE NEW MIXING TANK
AND EMERGENCY
SHUT-OFF VALVES.
♪♪
FEELS GOOD.
I LIKE THAT.
I GUESS JUST LET IT RUN
FOR A WHILE
AND SEE HOW HOT
IT WILL GET.
IT'S GONNA BE A MATTER
OF JUST FINE-TUNING IT.
AFTER INJURING
ONE OF HIS CREW,
DUSTIN'S NOT GOING
TO INJURE ANOTHER.
I'M GONNA TAKE ALL THE RISK
RIGHT NOW.
IF ANYBODY ELSE IS GONNA GET
HURT, IT HAD BETTER BE ME.
♪♪
[ Line ringing ]
-Hey.
-HEY, MY UGLY WIFE.
WHAT YOU DOING, MY BABY?
I'm just waiting for you.
I WENT TO GO WALK KANDA
RIGHT NOW,
AND, OH, MY GOSH, MY WOUNDS ARE
GETTING A LITTLE BIT SENSITIVE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
WHEN YOU GET DOWN HERE,
YOU CAN WHATCHACALIT --
YOU CAN BABY ME THEN, HUH?
-I love you very much.
-I LOVE YOU, TOO.
AND GIVE MY BABY A KISS
FROM ME, PLEASE.
I will.
WHAT WILL PUT THE CHERRY ON TOP
OF THIS SUNDAE RIGHT NOW
IS THAT MY WIFE'S RIGHT HERE
GIVING ME A HUG AND PUTTING
THE CREAM ON MY BACK.
AND I WILL TAKE FULL ADVANTAGE
OF IT, TOO, MAN.
I'LL BE LIKE, "OH, I'M HURTING.
OH, GO GET ME THIS.
OH, MASSAGE MY FEET."
BOY, YOU BETTER BELIEVE
I'LL TAKE FULL ADVANTAGE OF IT.
♪♪
Narrator:
AFTER CARLOS GOT BURNED,
DUSTIN'S CALLED "TIME"
ON GOLD MINING
UNTIL HE'S TESTED
THE NEW HOT-WATER SYSTEM.
♪♪
GONNA BE OUR FIRST TEST DIVE
SINCE CARLOS GOT BURNED.
HOPEFULLY WE GOT ALL THE BUGS
WORKED OUT OF THIS.
All right.
-No.
-Okay.
DUSTIN:
Paul! Shut it off!
Okay.
Hell, yeah.
Narrator:
DUSTIN RACKS UP 30 YARDS OF
GRAVEL THROUGH THE SLUICE BOX.
All right,
you coming up?
Good dive today, man.
Good dive.
All right. Comms off.
Off comms.
SOME GOOD TENDING TODAY, MAN.
I APPRECIATE YOU.
NO WORRIES.
[BLEEP] GOOD JOB,
STUD.
ACTUALLY STACKING UP.
WE WERE STARTING TO GET BACK
INTO OUR GROOVE TODAY.
EVERYTHING CLICKED.
WE HAVE SO MANY DIFFERENT
CONTROLS NOW
THAT THE HOT WATER
CAN BE SHUT OFF
SO MANY DIFFERENT WAYS TO YOU
THAT NO ONE SHOULD BE
IN DANGER ANYMORE.
I NEED CARLOS TO COME BACK
OUT HERE AFTER HE'S HEALED UP.
I'M SORRY IT HAPPENED,
AND I FEEL REALLY BAD ABOUT IT.
BUT WHEN HE COMES BACK
AND GETS IN THAT WATER,
I WANT HIM TO BE
100% CONFIDENT
HE CAN GET IN THAT WATER
WITHOUT GETTING BURNED AGAIN.
IT'LL MAKE CARLOS HAPPY TO HEAR
THAT WE'VE GOT ALL THIS SOLVED.
WE'RE READY FOR CARLOS
TO COME BACK.
WE SURE MISS HIM.
Narrator:
AFTER A TOUGH WEEK,
THEY'VE DREDGED SIX FEET
TO BEDROCK,
AND IT'S TIME TO SEE IF
THERE'S ANY GOLD IN THE MATS.
IF THERE'S ANY GOLD IN THIS,
IT'S GONNA BE FLOOD GOLD
'CAUSE IT'S RIGHT
OFF THE TOP,
AND IT'S NOT GONNA BE
A WHOLE BUNCH,
BUT IT'LL BE A GOOD SIGN
TO TELL US
IF THE GOLD'S SITTING
IN THIS AREA.
WE NEED TO KNOW IF THE
GOLD'S SLOWING DOWN HERE.
HERE COMES CASEY.
CASEY, COME HELP ME OUT HERE.
Casey: ALL RIGHT.
♪♪
THIS IS OUR CONCENTRATE.
HOPEFULLY,
WE GOT SOME GOLD IN IT.
Narrator: WES RUNS THE
CONCENTRATE THROUGH THE MACHINE
HE DESIGNED
AND BUILT HIMSELF.
THE ROCKS AND GRAVEL DROP OUT
THE END OF THE TROMMEL,
AND THE GOLD COLLECTS
IN THE MATS.
-WE HAVE GOLD IN THERE, FRED.
-YEAH, FRED.
-I'M SURE WE DO.
-WE FOUND GOLD.
Wes:
SERIOUSLY, MAN, LOOK AT THAT.
HEY, IT'S THE FIRST TEST.
IT'S OUR FIRST CLEAN-OUT,
SO IF WE'VE GOT
ANY AMOUNT OF GOLD AT ALL,
IT'S GOOD.
Narrator: WES PANS THE GOLD
FROM DUSTIN'S DREDGE,
AND FRED PANS
HIS OWN CONCENTRATE.
IT'S INCREDIBLE HOW IT JUST --
IT WILL STAY IN ONE PLACE.
ALL THE LITTLE TOP STUFF
JUST COMES RIGHT OUT THE SIDES.
FRED, CHECK THIS OUT.
GOT SOME GOOD COLOR THERE.
HELL, YEAH.
Fred: WE GOT A COUPLE
OF LITTLE CHUNKY PIECES
IN THERE THAT LOOK
PRETTY GOOD TO ME.
THEIRS IS LIKE GROUND-UP
SALT AND PEPPER.
Narrator: DUSTIN'S DREDGE
PRODUCED MORE GOLD,
BUT FRED'S GOLD
IS CHUNKIER.
MAN, THAT'S NOT BAD
FOR THE FIRST CLEAN-OUT, GUYS.
CHECK IT OUT.
THIS IS DAMN GOOD.
I'M GLAD THIS IS ON THE TOP,
RIGHT IN THE SURFACE.
THIS IS ALL FLOOD GOLD,
AND I'M EXCITED ABOUT THIS.
I THINK IT'S TIME FOR US
TO GET DOWN
AND FIND OUT
WHAT'S ACTUALLY DOWN THERE.
WE GOT TO GET BACK DOWN
TO WHERE WE WERE.
I DIDN'T EXPECT TO SEE THAT MUCH
IN THE OVER-BURDEN.
NOT AT ALL.
I DON'T CARE IF IT'S SMALL GOLD
OR BIG GOLD.
I JUST WANT A LOT OF GOLD.
AND LET'S GET
A WHOLE BUNCH MORE.
♪♪
Narrator: COMING UP...
-WOW. WHAT THE HELL'S THAT?
-THAT'S THE BEAR.
THIS BEAR TRIED TO GET
IN MY [BLEEP] DANG TENT!
THIS BEAR'S WATCHING US
RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE WE'RE HERE
IN THEIR BACKYARD.
HOLY [BLEEP] WATER
IS SINKING THE FRONT DOWN.
WE'VE GOT TO GET
THAT SMALL DREDGE UP.
UP! UP!
WHOA!WHOA!