Fred:
HOLY [BLEEP]
Dustin:
IT IS NO JOKE RIGHT NOW.
WE DON'T GET THEM BARGES UP,
WE'RE GONNA LOSE THEM BOTH.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S MOVE FRED'S DREDGE DOWN.
RAISE THAT FRONT UP.
WE NEED TO PICK IT UP WITH
THE NOSE UP A LITTLE BIT ON IT.
WE'RE GOING FOR IT!
COMING UP SLIGHTLY.
COMING UP.
WHOA!
-YO!
FRED, YOU GETTING
IN THE WATER TODAY?
YEAH.
EVEN IF IT GETS TOO DAMN COLD.
IF YOU PISS ME OFF,
I'M GONNA REACH OVER
AND CUT YOUR AIR LINE.
HOLY [BLEEP]
Carlos: THIS BEAR TRIED TO GET
IN MY [BLEEP] DANG TENT.
[BLEEP] BEAR!
WE'RE IN HIS BACKYARD.
CARRY YOUR GUNS.
EVERYBODY, BE SAFE,
BECAUSE YOU'RE BEING STALKED.
Paul: AH, DUDE, I SEE A LITTLE
PIECE OF GOLD DOWN HERE
SITTING ON A ROCK.
-WE'RE BACK AT IT.
WE'RE CATCHING GOLD.
THE DEEPER WE GO,
THE BETTER IT'S GETTING.
-WHOO!
-IT'S GREAT!
--Captions by VITAC--
www.vitac.com
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
DISCOVERY COMMUNICATIONS
♪♪
Dustin: I'VE SPENT SO MUCH MONEY
ON THIS PLACE.
IT NEEDS TO PAY OFF.
IN ORDER TO JUST
GET THINGS DONE,
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
TO DOUBLE DOWN,
BECAUSE WE'RE GONNA
RUN OUT OF TIME, MAN.
WE'VE GOT US ABOUT
A 6-FOOT HOLE,
BUT I'D LIKE THAT HOLE TO BE
15 FOOT BY THE END OF THIS WEEK.
I KNOW THAT'S
A LOT TO ASK,
BUT WE NEED TO GET DOWN
TO THE BOTTOM OF THIS
AND FIND OUT WHAT THE HELL
IS DOWN THERE, MAN.
Narrator: THE DAKOTA BOYS
ARE 3 WEEKS INTO THEIR SEARCH
FOR A DEPOSIT OF GOLD THAT WILL
MAKE THEM ALL MILLIONAIRES.
THEY'RE DOWN A MAN,
BUT THEY'RE NOT GIVING UP
ON THEIR TREASURE HUNT.
SO, CARLOS GOT BURNT,
AND HE'S OUT RIGHT NOW.
WE HAVE TO MAKE SURE
THAT NEVER HAPPENS AGAIN.
LAST WEEK,
CARLOS WAS SEVERELY BURNED
WHEN DUSTIN'S DREDGE SENT
SCALDING WATER TO HIS DIVE SUIT.
-OH, MY [BLEEP]
-UGH!
Dustin:
HE GOT BURNED.
WE'VE GOT TO GET HIM
TO THE HOSPITAL.
HE HAS NO CHOICE,
BUT HE HAS TO GO.
HE GOT SECOND-DEGREE BURNED
IN ABOUT FOUR PLACES.
Carlos: THAT PAIN WAS
SO UNDESCRIBABLE HOT.
I HAD WHITE LIGHT JUST SHOOTING
THROUGH MY WHOLE BODY.
Wes: WELL, RIGHT NOW, WE'VE GOT
ALL OF OUR HEAT SYSTEMS
TAKEN CARE OF.
SO, WE WON'T HAVE ANY MORE
MISHAPS WITH THAT,
AND I THINK CARLOS SHOULD
BE BACK PRETTY SOON.
WE REALLY NEED HIM BACK.
Fred: WE'VE BEEN BETTING
A LOT OF MONEY ON THIS.
I THINK,
WORKING WITH TWO DREDGES,
I DON'T SEE ANY REASON WE CAN'T
BE RIGHT BACK WHERE WE WERE
WHEN WE FINISHED
OUR SEASON LAST SEASON.
YOU GUYS READY
TO GET THE GOLD?
-YEAH.
-READY TO GET THE GOLD.
[ INDISTINCT TALKING,
AFFIRMING ]
♪♪
Narrator: THEY'RE DREDGING
IN ONE OF ALASKA'S
MOST TREACHEROUS CREEKS,
DIGGING BENEATH
THE FREEZING WHITE WATER
THROUGH 15 FEET
OF ROCKS AND GRAVEL
TO GET TO
THE BEDROCK GOLD BELOW.
FRED, YOU GETTING
IN THE WATER TODAY?
YEAH. EVEN IF IT GETS
TOO DAMN COLD.
IF YOU PISS ME OFF,
I'M GONNA REACH OVER
AND CUT YOUR AIR LINE.
Fred: FIRE IT UP!
LET'S GO!
♪♪
-THE ENGINES ARE RUNNING.
-YEAH.
I FEEL LIKE WE'RE GETTING
READY TO GO TO BATTLE.
[ IMITATES MACHINE
WHIRRING ]
Narrator: THE CREW'S
LATEST RECRUIT, CASEY MORGAN,
HAS 10 YEARS EXPERIENCE
GOLD MINING IN ARIZONA.
Casey: I DON'T WANT TO MESS UP,
BECAUSE YOU MESS UP.
THIS PLACE WILL CHEW YOU UP
AND SPIT YOU OUT SO FAST.
WE HAVE ALL THE ELEMENTS
GOING AGAINST US --
A CURRENT THAT CAN COME UP,
BEARS THAT ARE COMING DOWN.
AND FROM WHAT I'M HEARING,
THERE'S ALREADY ONE MAN DOWN
FROM A SERIOUS INJURY.
♪♪
Man:
HEY! CARLOS!
CARLOS MADE IT!
Carlos: WHOO!
[BLEEP] YEAH, DUDE!
GIVE ME THE GOLD!
[ LAUGHS ] YEAH!
WELCOME BACK, MAN!
THAT'S JUST THE WAY I LIKE
TO SEE IT, RIGHT HERE, MAN.
-HEY!
-WE DEFINITELY MISSED YOU.
HAPPY TO BE BACK.
[BLEEP] YEAH.
Narrator: CARLOS IS ON
DOCTOR'S ORDERS NOT TO DIVE
UNTIL HIS
SECOND-DEGREE BURNS HEAL.
YOU GUYS NEED
A HAMMER AND WRENCH.
THAT'S ALL I CAN DO
RIGHT NOW, MAN.
THAT'S IT.
THAT'S ALL I CAN DO.
THAT'S A BIG HELP, MAN.
IT'S DAMN GOOD
TO HAVE YOU BACK.
-YEAH.
-HELL YEAH.
WE'VE GOT TO HAVE THE HELP.
WE NEEDED THE HELP.
Dustin: WELL, I THOUGHT I KILLED
CARLOS, AND NOW HE'S BACK.
HE'S A BIG PART
OF THIS SITUATION HERE.
I NEED HIS HELP.
HEY, HEY, HEY.
LET'S GO.
COME ON.
LET'S GET THIS [BLEEP] TOGETHER.
Narrator:
74-YEAR-OLD FRED HURT
IS THE CREW'S
MOST EXPERIENCED DIVER.
Fred:
IT'S GONNA BE A LONG WEEK.
I HOPE EVERYBODY
IS PREPARED FOR IT.
I WANT TO GO AS HARD AS YOU CAN
OUT TO THE MIDDLE.
Narrator:
DIVING ALONGSIDE FRED
IS DUSTIN'S
RIGHT-HAND MAN, PAUL.
YEAH.
I'D SAY GO DEEP.
I'D SAY GO REAL DEEP
RIGHT HERE.
THE BIGGER ROCKS
ARE GONNA COME, SO...
-YEAH, I'LL HAVE THE BASKET.
-...BE ON GUARD.
I MIGHT BE ABLE TO GET
RIGHT HERE AND GET ME
A TUNNEL GOING DOWN.
OKAY.
LET'S SADDLE UP, BOYS.
LET'S GO DIVE.
OH [BLEEP]
THAT'S COLD ON
THE [BLEEP] FEET.
Narrator: LAST WEEK'S HOT-WATER
DISASTER COST VALUABLE TIME.
NOW THEY NEED A FULL WEEK
WITH BOTH DREDGES
TO GET BACK ON TRACK.
Paul: GO AHEAD!
Narrator: DUSTIN'S PLAN -- USING
TWO DREDGES AND TWO DIVERS,
THEY'LL PUMP OUT 15 FEET
OF ROCKS AND GRAVEL
TO GET TO A POCKET OF GOLD
ON THE BEDROCK BELOW.
Dustin: TOGETHER,
WE'RE GETTING GOLD.
Narrator: THE 6-INCH HOSE
SUCKS OUT ALL THE GRAVEL
AND ANY GOLD
UP TO THE DREDGE,
BUT ROCKS BIGGER THAN 6 INCHES
HAVE TO BE HAULED OUT BY HAND.
WES SENDS IN
THE ROCK BASKET.
Dustin:
GOT A WINCH OVER THERE THAT'LL
PULL OVER 4,000 POUNDS EASY.
THIS IS THE STRONGEST WINCH
WE'VE EVER HAD.
WE'LL PUT IT TO THE TEST
WHEN WE GET SOME HUGE ROCKS.
YEAH, WE GOT OUR FIRST BASKET
OF ROCKS UP.
OUR NEW WINCH SYSTEM SEEMS TO BE
HOLDING UP PRETTY WELL.
Dustin: FRED'S COME ACROSS
A PRETTY BIG ROCK.
AND IF WE CAN'T
MOVE THESE ROCKS,
THEN, YOU JUST
CAN'T DREDGE THEM.
WELL, WE'RE WORKING ON
GETTING THE BASKET BACK, FRED.
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM HERE?
Rich: THIS IS AWFUL SLOW,
TO DO IT LIKE THIS.
WE'VE HAD PROBLEMS
GETTING OUR ROCKS OUT.
WE'VE GOT ONE BASKET,
TWO CREWS, NOW.
SO, WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
COME UP WITH ANOTHER IDEA.
Dustin: GETTING [BLEEP]
STRESSED OUT!
Carlos: I'M OUT OF CONTROL,
IN MY HEAD, RIGHT NOW.
THAT'S [BLEEP]
I TELL YOU.
Narrator:
BY THE END OF THE DAY,
RISKING THEIR LIVES
ON THE ROCKY CREEK BED,
THEY'VE DUG DOWN
LESS THAN A FOOT.
WE'RE GETTING AHEAD OF OURSELF
TRYING TO START DREDGING
WITHOUT SETTING OUR
[BLEEP] UP.
IF WE COULD SPEED IT UP SOMEHOW,
THEN WE NEED TWO TYPES OF SLEDS,
TWO BASKETS
OR WHATEVER THE HELL IT IS.
WHAT WE'RE DOING RIGHT NOW
IS NOT WORKING.
♪♪
Fred:
WHAT THE HELL?
CARLOS, YOU'VE GOT BEAR PAWS
ON YOUR TENT, MAN.
Man: THERE'S PAWS RIGHT THERE
ON YOUR WALL, BUDDY.
Carlos:
WHAT THE HELL?
Carlos: THIS BEAR TRIED TO GET
IN MY [BLEEP] DANG TENT.
BASTARD, MAN.
-THAT WASN'T BROKE.
-NO. IT WASN'T.
Man: IT IS NOW.
Wes: THERE'S BEAR MARKS UP
THERE, WHERE HE TRIED TO GET
ON THE ROOF
AND GET IN ON TOP.
Paul: JUST REMEMBER,
HE'S THE ALPHA PREDATOR
OF THIS TERRITORY
AROUND HERE.
HOPEFULLY, HE'S JUST A LITTLE
BEAR THAT WE CAN SCARE OFF.
IF WE'VE GOT
A BIG OLD GRIZZLY,
IT'S GONNA HAVE TO BE
A DIFFERENT STORY.
♪♪
Narrator:
BLACK BEARS AND GRIZZLIES
ARE SOUTHEAST ALASKA'S
TOP PREDATORS.
WITH MORE THAN ONE
EVERY SQUARE MILE,
THEY POSE A CONSTANT THREAT
TO ANYONE IN THEIR HABITAT.
Paul: HEY, CARLOS.
DUDE, WHAT IS THIS, MAN?
THAT'S OUR GAME CAM.
LIKE A [BLEEP] SECURITY
CAMERA FOR ANIMALS, HUH?
CAN SEE WHAT'S COMING IN.
I HOPE IT AIN'T A GRIZZLY.
THAT'S -- I'D RATHER
HAVE A BLACK BEAR.
WE CAN SCARE IT AWAY.
A GRIZZLY I DON'T KNOW ABOUT.
THIS IS, LIKE,
MOTION DETECTION?
YEAH.
THIS WILL GIVE US A GOOD IDEA
OF WHAT WE'RE GONNA
HAVE TO DEAL WITH.
OKAY.
-OH, YEAH.
IT'S ARMED
AND READY TO GO.
A SMART IDEA, BROTHER.
♪♪
EVERYWHERE WE HIKE, THERE'S
BEARS WATCHING US RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE WE'RE HERE
IN THEIR BACKYARD.
CARRY YOUR GUNS.
EVERYBODY, BE SAFE.
-BECAUSE YOU'RE BEING STALKED.
♪♪
Narrator:
IN ALASKA, THE DAKOTA BOYS'
HUNT FOR GOLD IS ON HOLD...
♪♪
Wes: THIS IS GONNA BE
OUR NEW ROCK-HAUL-OUT BASKET.
...WHILE FABRICATOR WES WORKS
ON A NEW ROCK-MOVING SYSTEM.
I'M THE MACGYVER OF THE GROUP.
I CAN TAKE ANYTHING
AND MAKE ANYTHING OF IT.
SO, I WENT AND SCROUNGED UP
AS MUCH HEAVY STEEL AS I COULD.
THESE TWO SLEDS,
I WANT THEM STRONG.
I DON'T WANT THEM TO BE ABLE
TO TEAR THEM UP.
Narrator:
THE DIVERS WERE STRUGGLING
WITH JUST ONE ROCK BASKET.
NOW, WES IS CONSTRUCTING
A PAIR OF OVERSIZED SLEDS.
♪♪
Wes: WE'RE GONNA PULL OUT
TONS OF ROCKS WITH TWO OF THEM.
THIS WILL PROBABLY HOLD
A 400 OR 500-POUND ROCK.
IF THEY CAN ROLL IT INTO
THIS THING, WE CAN PULL IT OUT.
THESE ARE REALLY CRUCIAL
TO OUR OPERATION.
EVERYTHING THAT WE CAN'T
GET OUT WITH A DREDGE,
WE'RE GONNA RELY
ON THESE THINGS.
THEY'RE JUST GONNA FILL THEM UP,
AND WE'RE GONNA PULL THEM OUT,
AND IT'S GONNA HELP US
FIND EVEN MORE GOLD.
♪♪
THIS IS GONNA SPEED UP
OUR PROCESS A LOT.
Man: HEY, PAUL, YOU'RE GONNA BE
CARRYING THOSE, RIGHT?
-YEP.
-OH, GOOD.
NOT A PROBLEM.
I'VE CARRIED HEAVIER WEIGHT
THAN THAT.
THAT THING IS LIGHT.
Narrator:
IT'S A MILE-AND-A-HALF TREK
FROM THE CAMP TO THE DIVE SITE.
Dustin: OH, THESE BASKETS
WEREN'T EASY TO GET HERE,
BUT THEY'RE HERE NOW.
-THANK [BLEEP]
OH, MAN.
THIS THING IS SO AWKWARD.
-WHOO.
-GOOD JOB, FELLAS.
GOOD JOB, MAN.
-I GOT TIRED WATCHING HIM.
Paul: OH, MAN.
THESE THINGS ARE HEAVY.
ENOUGH TO PUT ME
SWEATING PRETTY HARD.
[ LAUGHS ]
GOOD JOB, MAN.
-OH, YEAH.
WAY TO PUSH THROUGH.
MY LEGS ARE
ON FIRE RIGHT NOW.
Dustin:
ALL RIGHT, FELLAS. SO, WE'RE
GONNA START MOVING SOME ROCKS.
IT'S GONNA BE YOUR JOB
ALL DAY TODAY.
WE'RE GONNA MOVE ALL THESE
BOULDERS OUT OF THE WAY.
BACK TO DIVING.
MODIFY, MODIFY, MODIFY.
-MAKE WORK.
-MODIFY!
♪♪
Fred:
YOU GOING DOWN TODAY?
YEAH. YOU AND I
ARE SIDE BY SIDE TODAY.
Narrator: FATHER AND SON
WILL DIVE SIDE BY SIDE...
Man:
ALL RIGHT, HOT ROD.
...AS THEY TEST OUT
WES' NEW SLED BASKETS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
YEAH, HE'S BRAVE.
HE WANTS TO GO FOR IT.
♪♪
EXPERT DIVER CARLOS CAN'T
DIVE AGAIN UNTIL HIS BURNS HEAL.
TODAY, HE IS TENDING
DUSTIN'S DIVE.
-I LIKE IT.
-YEP.
Carlos: GOOD TO GO. GOOD TO GO.
GOOD TO GO BACK HERE.
♪♪
THE THING ABOUT EVERYTHING
IS HOW FAST
WE CAN GET THESE ROCKS OUT
AND GET DOWN TO THE BEDROCK.
Rich: ROGER.
ROGER, ROGER, ROGER.
Narrator: FRED AND DUSTIN
HAVE REMOVED A 3-FOOT LAYER
OF ROCKS AND BOULDERS,
LEAVING JUST 7 FEET BETWEEN THEM
AND THE GOLD-RICH BEDROCK.
FRED'S GETTING HIMSELF
A PRETTY GOOD HOLE DOWN THERE,
SLOWLY GETTING CLOSER
TO A PAYDAY, HOPEFULLY.
♪♪
Fred: OH, THEM ROCKS
WILL WHIP YOUR BUTT.
WE'RE GONNA
CALL IT A DAY.
KNOW I SURE
CALLED IT A DAY.
I'M TIRED. [ LAUGHS ]
Rich: SOMETIMES, YOU FORGET
HOW OLD FRED IS.
HE WAS IN THERE
PRACTICALLY ALL DAY LONG.
IT'S PRETTY IMPRESSIVE.
I'M UP.
HOW'D IT GO, FRED?
THAT BASKET HELPED ME A WHOLE
BUNCH, AND THE LITTLE SLEDS.
THE WHOLE SYSTEM
IS A WHOLE LOT BETTER.
Dustin: YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE
HOW FAST YOU COULD DIVE
WITH TWO BASKETS
RIGHT NOW.
WELL, IF OUR DIVE
STAYS THIS GOOD,
WE'RE GONNA BE DOWN
TO GOLD IN NO TIME.
♪♪
Wes: SO, I'VE GOT TO SEE
WHAT THEY GOT DONE TODAY.
-HOW DEEP IS IT?
-[BLEEP]
Wes: I GOT 9 FOOT, THERE,
IN THE MIDDLE, NOW.
Dustin: NOW, WE'RE
GETTING SOMEWHERE.
WE'VE GOT HEADWAY
THIS TIME.
IT'S AWESOME, MAN.
Dustin: I DIDN'T THINK IT
WAS POSSIBLE, BUT WE DID IT.
COME OUT AND
FIXED THE PROBLEM.
I THINK IT'S TIME
TO CALL IT QUITS.
WE'RE GONNA FIX
OUR EQUIPMENT,
MAKE SURE IT'S READY TO GO
FOR EARLY TOMORROW MORNING.
♪♪
Man: WOW, THE WATER
MUST REALLY BE UP.
LOOK AT IT
FLOWING IN OVER THERE.
-HOLY [BLEEP]
-IT'S MOVING.
Narrator: NEXT DAY,
THE WATER LEVEL IS UP 2 FEET.
MAN, I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT THIS [BLEEP]
THAT IS DEATH WATER.
IF YOU FALL IN THAT,
YOU'RE DONE, MAN.
THIS STUFF
WILL KILL YOU.
I DIDN'T COME HERE
TO DIE, MAN.
I CAME HERE TO GET RICH.
GOD, LOOK. THE WATER IS GOING
OVER HIS [BLEEP] DREDGE.
CARLOS, HOLD UP.
HOLD UP. HOLD UP.
Y'ALL, SHUCK YOUR GEAR
AS QUICK AS POSSIBLE!
IT'S GETTING
A LINE ON THERE.
CARLOS, YOU CAN SEE IF
YOU CAN FIND A DECENT ROPE
THAT WOULD REACH FROM HERE
ALL THE WAY ACROSS OVER THERE.
Fred: THE BIG BARGE,
THE FRONT END IS UNDERWATER.
THIS IS A DISASTROUS SITUATION,
RIGHT HERE.
WE DON'T GET THEM BARGES UP,
WE'RE GONNA LOSE THEM BOTH.
♪♪
Fred: HOLY COW!
Dustin: HOLY [BLEEP]
IT IS NO JOKE RIGHT NOW.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT SOMEBODY
FALLING INTO THIS DAMN WATER
AND GETTING THEIR ASS
KICKED AND DYING.
CAN YOU IMAGINE WHAT WOULD
HAPPEN IF A TREE CAME THROUGH?
YEAH, IT WOULD
WIPE US OUT.
Narrator:
IN THE CHILL CAP MOUNTAINS,
HOT WEATHER IS SENDING
4,000 GALLONS OF SNOWMELT
THROUGH THE DAKOTA BOYS'
MINE SITE EVERY SECOND.
Fred: BOTH DREDGES,
WATER IS SINKING THE FRONT DOWN.
WE'VE GOT TO GET
THAT SMALL DREDGE UP.
Dustin: GONNA WANT TO
GO DOWN CREEK
AND DESTROY EVERYTHING I HAVE --
BOTH DREDGES, EVERYTHING.
WE'VE GOT A WINCH RIGHT AT
THE END OF THE DOCK, HERE.
RAISE THAT FRONT UP.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S MOVE FRED'S DREDGE.
Fred: WE HAVE A FOUR-FIVE PICKUP
ON THAT BARGE.
WE NEED TO PICK IT UP WITH
THE NOSE UP A LITTLE BIT ON IT.
Carlos:
WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO IS,
WE'RE GONNA PUT A PULLEY
ON THIS FREAKING SUPPORT ROPE,
RUN IT DOWN TO THE DREDGE,
AND JUST LIFT IT UP.
WE'RE NOT TRYING TO LIFT
THE DREDGE UP ALL THE WAY OUT.
WE'RE JUST TRYING TO LIFT IT UP
JUST A LITTLE BIT,
JUST SO IT'S NOT SINKING.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
-COMING UP SLIGHTLY.
-COMING UP.
-HO!
-RIGHT AT THE EDGE.
Dustin:
STOP, STOP, STOP.
Fred: POPPED ONE OF
THE WEIGHTS OFF.
LOOKS LIKE WE NEED TO
TIGHTEN UP THE CABLES
IN THE BACK
A LITTLE BIT.
GONNA LET THAT DOWN
JUST A LITTLE BIT.
WE'RE IN A PRETTY
GOOD STRAIN, THERE.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE HOLDING.
HOLD IT.
NO. DO NOT COME DOWN.
Man: I THINK IT
LOOKS OKAY, FRED.
COMING UP
A LITTLE BIT.
Man: EASY!
COMING UP.
-THE EDGE LOOKS GOOD.
-YEAH, NO MORE!
Dustin: I THINK
WE'RE GOOD, RIGHT?
ACTUALLY, IT'S SITTING
PRETTY DAMN GOOD, ACTUALLY.
Carlos: YEAH. THAT'S PRETTY GOOD
RIGHT THERE WHERE IT'S AT.
-THAT'S ONE.
-YO, LET'S MOVE THAT OTHER ONE!
Narrator:
NEXT UP, DUSTIN'S DREDGE.
Dustin:
COME HELP ME, PAUL!
COPY.
WHOA!
Narrator: THE HOOK THEY NEED
TO RAISE IT
IS FIXED TO A BOULDER RIGHT IN
THE MIDDLE OF THE RAGING CREEK.
Man: THIS IS SUPER
DANGEROUS FOR US.
WE'RE GONNA
HAVE TO UNDO THIS.
THEY CAN GRAB MAYBE
THE FRONT END WITH THAT
BY SNATCHING IT OFF THE SIDE
AND PICK UP ON IT A LITTLE BIT.
WHY WOULD YOU PUT THAT [BLEEP]
THING UP LOOSE LIKE THAT?
Dustin: EVER DO SOMETHING AND
WHILE YOU'RE DOING IT SAYING,
"THIS IS STUPID.
THIS IS STUPID"?
RIGHT NOW,
IT'S ONE OF THEM TIMES.
-[BLEEP] MADMEN, DUDE.
-YOU'VE GOT TO PULL ON IT.
-THAT'LL WORK.
-HEAVE!
IT'S UP!
ATTABOY.
CAN YOU BRING IT UP
A LITTLE BIT?
I GOT IT.
UGH!
-THANK YOU.
-PERFECT!
Dustin: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S SEE WHAT WE CAN DO HERE.
EVERYBODY,
OUT OF THE WATER!
IT'S TOO STUPID NOW.
YOU'RE NOT BRAVE ANYMORE.
YOU'RE DUMB.
UP, UP, UP.
♪♪
-THAT'S ABOUT IT.
-THAT'S IT.
I THINK THAT'S PERFECT
RIGHT THERE.
IT LOOKS GOOD.
GOT THE NOSE END UP.
Dustin: THANK YOU, GUYS!
LEAVE IT RIGHT THERE!
WOO-HOO!
-DAMN!
♪♪
I WONDER HOW OLD
I'M GONNA BE
WHEN I STOP DOING
THIS STUPID [BLEEP]
Narrator:
THE HOT SUMMER SUN IS SENDING
500 TONS OF RAGING MELTWATER
DOWN THE CREEK
EVERY MINUTE.
THE DAKOTA BOYS
NEED THE LEVEL TO DROP
BEFORE IT'S SAFE
TO DIVE AGAIN.
Fred: LOOKS LIKE
EVERYTHING SURVIVED.
BOTH THE DREDGES
ARE SAFE AND SOUND.
IT WORKED.
FREAKING HOT DAY
TODAY, MAN.
I'VE NEVER SEEN IT SO HOT
IN ALASKA.
THIS MORNING,
IT WARMED UP.
IT'S KEEPING
THAT WATER UP.
IT'S MELTING OFF THE ICE CAP
UP ON THE MOUNTAIN UP THERE,
AND THE WATER IS, AGAIN,
TODAY, OUT OF CONTROL.
Dustin: I DON'T THINK
WE'RE DIVING, MAN.
YEAH, IT JUST LOOKS LIKE
THE WATER IS A LITTLE TOO CRAZY.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
HOW MANY TIMES DO WE
HAVE TO START OVER?
WHEN THE SUN COMES OUT,
THE WATER GOES UP.
WHEN IT RAINS TOO MUCH,
WHEN THERE'S A LANDSLIDE,
THE WATER GOES UP.
JUST NEVER ENDS.
WES, HOW DEEP IS IT?
Wes: DUSTIN,
THE HOLE FILLED IN.
WHAT? YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
THE WHOLE THING FILLED IN?
COMPLETELY.
IT'S TOTALLY GONE.
IT WAS 9 FEET DEEP.
IT'S ONLY 6 INCHES.
ALL THE DREDGING WE DID
SO FAR JUST GOT COVERED UP.
HOW MANY TIMES CAN YOU JUST
CHASE AND CHASE AND CHASE?
THE HOLE FILLED BACK IN.
EITHER STUPID
OR JUST DETERMINED,
AND I THINK I PASSED DETERMINED
A LONG TIME AGO.
Narrator: SNOWMELT HAS
CARRIED DOWN TONS OF GRAVEL,
ROCKS, AND BOULDERS, COMPLETELY
FILLING THE DIVE HOLE.
A MONTH'S WORK WIPED OUT
IN JUST 24 HOURS.
THAT'S WHAT IT LOOKED LIKE
WHEN THE FLOOD CAME THROUGH
LAST SEASON,
RAGING JUST AS BAD.
Dustin: EVERY CHANCE YOU GET
TO DIG A HOLE, YOU DIG.
SO, THERE'S NO "WE HAVE
A WHOLE SUMMER AHEAD OF US,"
BECAUSE WE DON'T.
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
START OVER AGAIN.
♪♪
ANY HOLE THAT ANY DIVER
PUT DOWN THERE
IS GONE A LONG TIME AGO.
WE'VE HEARD NOTHING
BUT HUGE ROCK.
WE'RE TALKING 2,000-
OR 3,000-POUND BOULDERS ROLLING.
THEY MAKE, LIKE, THUNDER.
WHEN WE FINALLY GET BACK
DOWN TO CHECK IT,
THERE'S GONNA BE NOTHING
BUT HUGE BOULDERS
ALL OVER THAT BOTTOM.
TOMORROW, HOPEFULLY,
THE WATER IS DOWN A LITTLE BIT,
AND WE CAN GO DIVING.
LET'S SEND THEM HOME!
-UGH.
-ANOTHER DAY.
♪♪
Fred: HEY.
WE HAD MORE THAN
THE NORMAL VISITORS.
-OH, NO.
-GOD.
-FREAKING BEAR, MAN.
Narrator: BACK AT CAMP,
MORE BEAR TROUBLE.
EVERY DAY, I WONDER,
"WHAT KIND OF CRAZY [BLEEP]
GONNA HAPPEN TODAY?"
YOU GET THREE OR FOUR OF THEM
IN HERE, THOUGH,
AND THEY'LL TAKE
THE TENTS DOWN.
THEY'LL TAKE
EVERYTHING DOWN.
YOU GIVE THAT CAR
TO THE GAME CAM?
Man: COOL.
LET'S CHECK IT OUT.
♪♪
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S CHECK IT OUT.
Man:
SEE WHAT'S ON IT.
♪♪
-THERE IT GOES.
-WOW.
-WHOA.
-WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
-THAT'S THE BEAR.
-HOLY [BLEEP]
Man: OH, HE PULLED
OUR [BLEEP] OUT.
LOOK AT HIM.
HE'S GOT SOME STRENGTH.
HE ISN'T SCARED OF NOTHING,
IS HE?
NO.
Dustin: WE'RE IN
HIS BACKYARD.
YOU'VE GOT TO BELIEVE THAT
HE'S JUST ON THE OUTSKIRTS,
KNOWING WHAT WE'RE DOING,
LISTENING OR SMELLING FOR US
OR WHATEVER HE'S DOING.
AND THEN, AS SOON AS WE LEAVE,
HE COMES IN THE CAMP.
HE'S WATCHING US MORE
THAN WE'RE WATCHING HIM.
♪♪
IF IT'S NOT THE WATER
TRYING TO GET US OR THE FLOODS,
IT'S THE DAMN BEARS COMING OUT
AND DESTROYING MY GEAR.
WE ORDERED UP
A BEAR FENCE.
YEAH, IT'S A LIGHTWEIGHT
ELECTRIC FENCE
THAT WE'RE GONNA SET UP.
IT GIVES THE BEAR A LITTLE BIT
OF A SHOCK
WHEN IT MESSES WITH IT.
I DON'T WANT TO KILL HIM,
SO, THIS IS A GOOD WAY
TO KEEP HIM OUT, MAN.
THIS WAY, WE DON'T HAVE TO
SHOOT HIM, AND I LOVE IT, MAN.
-ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
-WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO BE AWARE,
AND KEEP AN EYE OUT
FOR THIS BEAR.
Man: STAY ALERT.
STAY ALIVE.
♪♪
SO, WE GOT HAMMERED
AGAIN, GUYS.
THE HOLE GOT FILLED IN,
AND IT'S HEARTBREAKING
WHAT HAPPENED.
IT FILLED IN.
BUT I DON'T SEE
ANY OTHER CHOICE
BUT TO GO RIGHT BACK DOWN
TO WHERE WE WERE.
YOU THINK ABOUT
ALL THE WEEKS AND WEEKS
AND WEEKS
THAT WE DUG THAT THING.
Narrator:
DUSTIN HURT GAMBLED $75,000
ON HIS SEARCH FOR GOLD
AT McKINLEY CREEK.
BUT ALMOST A MONTH
INTO THE SEASON,
THEIR MINE SITE WAS FILLED IN
BY A FLASH FLOOD.
Man: OUR BIGGEST THING
IS GONNA BE MOTHER NATURE.
WE'VE GOT TO
BEAT MOTHER NATURE.
Dustin: HOPEFULLY, THE WATER
IS DONE, AND WE CAN GO DIVING.
LET'S GO
CHECK IT OUT, GUYS.
WE HAVE TO GET GOLD
THIS YEAR.
♪♪
Man: HOW'S IT LOOKING
DOWN THERE?
Man: YEAH!
LOOKS GOOD TO ME.
Fred:
THAT'S MORE LIKE IT!
THE WATER IS LOOKING GREAT.
THIS IS GOOD
DIVING WATER.
I'M HOPING WE CAN
GET BACK ON TRACK.
I HOPE WITHIN
THE END OF THE WEEK,
I'M DOWN TO 7 FEET.
WE'RE BACK ON.
LOOKS HAPPY AGAIN.
BACK TO WORK.
SHE'S PLAYING NICE TODAY,
VERY NICE.
WE'RE BEHIND SCHEDULE NOW,
SO WE NEED TO REALLY STEP UP
AND REALLY
DIG THIS HOLE.
WE NEED TO GET BACK DOWN
ALL THE WAY TO THE BOTTOM.
♪♪
Paul: GONNA TRY TO GET
A GOOD LONG DIVE IN TODAY.
Narrator: PAUL TAKES THE LEAD,
STARTING FROM ZERO,
TO GET DOWN TO
THE BEDROCK GOLD
15 FEET BELOW
THE CREEK BED.
♪♪
Dustin: YEAH.
PAUL IS A GREAT DREDGER,
AND I'M HOPING
THAT HE DOES AT LEAST
WHAT I CAN DO
DOWN THERE TODAY.
Paul: OH [BLEEP]
THIS IS A LARGE.
WELL, PUT IT ON,
AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
Rich: SO,
TODAY IS MY FIRST DAY.
THEY'LL SOON FIND OUT THAT
I'M NOT MUCH OF A GREENHORN
ONCE I GET ON
THAT DREDGE NOZZLE.
I JUST WANT TO
GET TO DREDGING.
I WANT TO GET
TO FINDING GOLD.
RICH HAS BEEN BEGGING
TO GET IN THE WATER.
I DISAPPOINTED HIM LAST WEEK
AND DIDN'T LET HIM GET IN.
I'LL GIVE HIM HIS WISH.
[ LAUGHS ]
Narrator:
SIX WEEKS AFTER LEAVING BEHIND
HIS COMPUTER-REPAIR BUSINESS,
RICH WILL DIVE THE WHITE WATERS
OF McKINLEY CREEK
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
YOU THE MAN
ON THAT THING OUT THERE.
Rich:
I'M GONNA TEAR IT UP.
THIS IS GONNA
KICK YOUR ASS TODAY.
YOU'RE GONNA GET
YOUR BUTT KICKED.
WELL, I WANTED TO DIVE.
ALWAYS KEEP YOUR
FEET DOWNSTREAM,
AND TRY TO KEEP THE NOZZLE
OUT AHEAD OF YOU.
DON'T PANIC.
-I WON'T.
AS SOON AS YOU PANIC,
YOU CAN'T BREATHE DOWN THERE.
THIS IS THE BEST IT'S GONNA
BE FOR YOU, RIGHT HERE.
HERE WE GO.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
FEEL GOOD?
YOU FEEL GOOD?
OKAY.
[ RICH BREATHING
THROUGH SCUBA MASK]
RICH IS IN PROBABLY THE CALMEST
WATER WE HAVE HERE, SO...
LOOKS LIKE HE'S A LITTLE TANGLED
UP IN EVERYTHING, THOUGH.
WELCOME TO ALASKA.
Narrator: BATTLING AGAINST
THE 12,000 GALLONS OF WATER
THAT FLOW DOWN THE CREEK
EVERY MINUTE,
ROOKIE MINER RICH
STRUGGLES TO MAKE PROGRESS.
TELL HIM,
GET A ROCK READY!
HE NEEDS TO
GET A ROCK.
HE CAN PUT IT
INSIDE THAT.
[BLEEP]
Narrator:
AFTER BARELY 2 HOURS
WRESTLING THE CURRENT,
RICH CALLS IT.
NOTHING HERE IS JUST
STRAIGHTFORWARD,
EASY, GOES AS PLANNED,
GOES THE WAY IT'S SUPPOSED TO.
Fred:
HE WAS HAVING A LITTLE...
LET'S JUST SAY A
"LEARNING-CURVE MOMENT" --
SOMETHING ABOUT
THE VISIBILITY.
AND, I MEAN, HEY, VISIBILITY
IS A BONUS OUT HERE.
RICH, I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THAT WAS ALL ABOUT,
ABOUT THE VISIBILITY.
KEEP THAT BASKET
RIGHT NEXT TO YOU.
Rich: ALL RIGHT.
JUST PULL THE THING UP THERE
WHERE YOU'RE GONNA WORK.
JUST FILL IT UP.
EVERYTHING RIGHT NOW
IS GOING TO [BLEEP]
♪♪
I GOT TO CHANGE THESE AT LEAST
IN THE MORNING AND AT NIGHT.
THESE THINGS GET INFECTED.
IT'S NO ONE'S FAULT
OTHER THAN MY OWN.
THE BETTER I
TAKE CARE OF IT,
THE QUICKER I CAN
GET BACK IN THE WATER.
I ALWAYS THINK ABOUT THE
MALFUNCTION OF THE HOT WATER,
OF LOSING HOT WATER,
AND GOING THROUGH HYPOTHERMIA,
YOU KNOW?
BUT IT DIDN'T HAPPEN
THAT WAY.
NEVER DID I EVER THOUGHT
OF THE REVERSE EFFECT,
OF BEING FREAKING BOILED UP.
I AIN'T NEVER THOUGHT
ABOUT THAT.
IT NEVER CAME INTO
MY HEAD ONCE.
I DON'T WANT THIS PAUSE
IN OUR OUTPUT OF WORK.
YOU CAN'T KEEP ME
OUT OF THE WATER. NO.
HELL NO. THAT'S MY JOB, MAN.
THAT'S WHAT I DO.
THAT'S WHO I AM.
THAT'S...I LIVE IN THE WATER.
THAT'S MY MAIN JOB.
I'M A DIVER, MAN.
I'M THEIR DIVER, SO...
I FREAKING MISSED THEM, MAN.
I MISSED THEM.
I FELT LIKE A --
WHAT YOU CALL IT --
A LONG-LOST DOG BEING REUNITED
WITH THEIR OWNERS AFTER 3 YEARS.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
Paul: LOOKS LIKE I'M GONNA HAVE
A GOOD DIVE TODAY.
IT'S ALL NICE AND CLEAR.
I CAN SEE THE BOTTOM,
MEANS IT'S TIME
TO GET IN THE WATER
AND FIND THE GOLD.
Narrator: THREE DAYS AGO,
A FLASH FLOOD
FILLED IN THEIR HOLE.
PAUL GOT THROUGH
3 FEET YESTERDAY.
THERE'S ANOTHER 12 FEET TO GO
TO GET TO BEDROCK GOLD.
WE'RE DIVING.
ALL RIGHT, BROTHER.
THE WATER'S LOOKING GOOD.
WE'VE GOT A DIVER DOWN.
PAUL, I'M HOPING THAT HE'S GONNA
REALLY GET THIS CLEANED OUT.
-YOU NERVOUS?
-YEAH.
-YEAH, HANG IN THERE.
-I'D BE LYING IF I SAID NO.
Narrator: YESTERDAY,
RICH ABORTED HIS DIVE.
NOW FRED GIVES HIM A SECOND
CHANCE TO PROVE HIMSELF.
SO...WE'RE GONNA GET BACK
DOWN THERE AND GET AFTER IT.
Dustin: EVERYBODY IS
WORKING TOGETHER,
IS GONNA GET ME THAT MUCH CLOSER
TO GOLD THAT MUCH FASTER.
YOU'VE GOT TO
FEEL YOUR WAY AROUND.
Rich: ARF, ARF.
Narrator: RICH HAS DREDGED
3 FEET OF ROCKS AND GRAVEL...
...AND PROVED HE CAN HANDLE
McKINLEY CREEK.
Carlos: RICH, WHAT'S THIS
3-HOUR [BLEEP] MAN?
WHAT THE [BLEEP]
IS THAT?
I'M JUST GETTING
STARTED, CARLOS.
[ LAUGHS ]
Fred:
HE GOT RIGHT BACK IN THAT WATER
AFTER BEING THROWN OFF A HORSE.
WITH TIME, HE WILL BE
A TOP-NOTCH DIVER.
I'M PROUD OF RICH.
AH, ONE MORE TIME.
Narrator: McKINLEY VETERAN PAUL
SHOWS NO SIGN OF STOPPING.
Dustin: WOW. FRED, YOU KNOW HE'S
STANDING UP RIGHT THERE, RIGHT?
Paul:
WHOO! YEAH, BABY.
APPARENTLY, PAUL CAN STAND UP
UNDERNEATH THE CURRENT
ABOUT 6 OR 7 FEET.
-YOU CAN SEE GOLD.
-[BLEEP] YEAH!
HE'S CHASING GOLD.
IT'S GREAT!
Narrator: PAUL RACKS UP THE
LONGEST DIVE OF THE SEASON --
6 1/2 HOURS IN THE WATER.
GREAT DIVE, THERE, PAUL!
Dustin: THAT'S A LOT OF
DAMN DREDGING YOU DID.
THAT WAS A LOT
OF [BLEEP]
LOOK WHAT HE DID, MAN.YEAH, I KNOW.
WHAT WAS COOL WAS SEEING THAT
GOLD LAYING ON THEM ROCKS, MAN.
EVERYTHING ELSE WAS
GOING IN THE NOZZLE,
AND IT JUST STAYED
RIGHT THERE
UNTIL I'D STICK
THE NOZZLE RIGHT ON IT.
THEN, IT'D SUCK THEM UP BUT...
-THAT'S AWESOME, MAN.
THAT'S SOME CRAZY ENDURANCE
YOU'VE GOT THERE, BUDDY.
CRAZY ENDURANCE, MAN.
I HEARD THEM ALL EXCITED
OVER THERE.
THEY MIGHT HAVE GOT
A LITTLE GOLD IN THE TRAY.
Dustin: WE GOT QUITE A BIT
OF GOLD IN HERE.
GOOD DIVE.
WE GOT GOLD, BROTHER.
QUITE A BIT PACKED UP
BENEATH THOSE RIPPLES.
-HELL YEAH!
-GOT SOME MORE IN THE MIDDLE.
CATCHING GOLD.
WE'RE CATCHING GOLD, BRO.
THE DEEPER WE GO,
THE BETTER IT'S GETTING.
I LIKE IT.
YEAH!
Dustin: SO, WE'RE GONNA
DO A CLEANUP.
PAUL IS AN ANIMAL.
HE DID THE MOST DREDGING
WE'VE DONE ALL YEAR.
7 FEET IS A DAMN GOOD START.
Paul: OH, I'M EXTREMELY
HAPPY TODAY.
IT DOESN'T GET
ANY BETTER THAN THAT.
WE'RE BACK AT IT.
♪♪
OH, FOR REALS, MAN?
DID YOU REALLY JUST STAND UP,
MAN, ON THE BOTTOM OF THAT HOLE,
MAN, AND HELD YOUR HAND UP?
SHOOT, IT WAS ABOUT, WHAT,
HOWEVER DEEP THAT IS, AT LEAST.
-[BLEEP]
-PRETTY DEEP, MAN.
6, A LITTLE OVER 6, 7 FEET.
Wes:
CHECK THIS OUT, GUYS.
WE GOT HALF AS MUCH GOLD AS WE
GOT THE WHOLE LAST SEASON, DUDE.
-WHAT?
-CHECK THAT OUT.
WE'RE IN A PERFECT AREA
RIGHT NOW.
-YEAH!
-OKAY.
YOU'RE RICH.
-I LIKE THAT.
WE WERE 15 FEET DEEP LAST YEAR
BEFORE WE GOT THIS MUCH GOLD.
-OKAY.
-WE DIDN'T GET
[BLEEP] LIKE THAT.
-BEAUTIFUL, MAN.
-WE'RE STILL DIGGING.
THAT'S SOME FINE GOLD,
ISN'T IT?
-HELL YEAH.
-WHEN WE GET DOWN,
THERE'S NO TELLING HOW MUCH
WE'RE GONNA GET OUT OF THERE.
YOU DON'T KNOW REALLY GET
THE BIG STUFF
TILL YOU HIT THE BEDROCK.
Dustin:
WELL, I'LL TELL YOU
BECAUSE WE'RE GONNA BE
DOWN THERE REAL SOON.
-UP AHEAD...
-COME ON, FRED.
WE'RE OUT HERE TO FIND
SOME GOLD -- LOTS OF IT.
WATCH OUT, FRED. THEY'RE
BRINGING A REAL HEAVY LOAD UP.
[ FRED SCREAMS ]
DEFINITION OF COURAGE -- BEING
AFRAID AND DOING IT ANYWAY.
Man: FEELING GOOD.
FROM THIS DAY FORWARD,
WE SHOULD GET REALLY GOOD GOLD.
-LOOK AT THAT. THIS IS AMAZING!
-THAT'S WHERE THE
GOLD IS GONNA BE.