Fred: BACK UP A LITTLE BIT.
BACK UP A LITTLE BIT.
-THAT LOOKS GOOD.
-ALL RIGHT. LET'S GO.
Wes: WHOO! COME ON.
Fred: YOUR TAG LINE!
THEY DIDN'T WANT A TAG LINE.
THEY WANT TO HOOK IT UP.
SO HOW THEY GOING TO HOOK UP
A THING OUT
THE MIDDLE OF THE WATER?
-I DON'T KNOW.
-BULL[BLEEP]!
I WANT IT RIGHT THERE
AGAINST THAT WALL.
-COPY THAT.
-I'M A LITTLE NERVOUS.
I AIN'T GOING TO LIE.
PAUL, I NEED YOU BACK
OVER HERE NOW!
NOW!
GO OVER HERE!
PAUL!
Paul: COME ON!
I GOT [BLEEP]. I GOT IT!
WHAT THE [BLEEP]
HAPPENED?
[ BLEEP ].
I MISSED MY CLIP.
TIGHTEN UP!
GO, GO, GO!
-NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
NO, NO, NO!
OH, [BLEEP].
HOLD ON!
THE INSPECTOR IS HERE.
-IT AIN'T LONG ENOUGH.
NOT LONG ENOUGH.
NOT LONG [BLEEP] ENOUGH.
WELL, FRED HAS GOT HIS IDEAS,
AND I'VE GOT MINE.
WHEN IT COMES DOWN TO IT,
I'M IN CHARGE.
OH, [BLEEP]!
-THE HELL IS THAT?
-THAT'S THE BEAR.
-WHAT THE [BLEEP]?
-GET BACK! GET!
GET OUT OF HERE!
THAT'S A WILD MAN.
AND YOU THOUGHT YOUR JOB
WAS HARD!
EXTREME DREDGING, BROTHER,
EXTREME DREDGING.
-WHOA!
-THE EAGLE HAS LANDED.
I'VE SEEN GOLD 15 FEET
DOWN IN THAT HOLE.
WE GOING TO GET IT THIS YEAR.
-WHOO!
-THAT'S GOLD.
THAT'S GOLD!
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
DISCOVERY COMMUNICATIONS
♪♪
Fred: ALL RIGHT.
I'M GETTING READY TO DO THIS
DEATH-DEFYING ACT OUT HERE.
IT'S ONLY A 250-FOOT
STRAIGHT-DOWN FALL.
FIRST TIME ACROSS THIS YEAR,
GREAT, MAN.
YOO!
I CAN'T WAIT TO GET OUT THERE
AND GET SOME GOLD.
THAT'S WHAT IT'S ALL ABOUT!
LET'S GO.
YA-HOO-HOO-HOO!
WOW!
WHAT A SIGHT.
BOY, IT IS BEAUTIFUL.
LET'S GO GET SOME GOLD!
BE SAFE, FRED.
Narrator: THE DAKOTA BOYS,
FRED AND DUSTIN HURT,
-HOO!
-ARE BACK IN ALASKA...
Dustin:
TIME TO GET SOME GOLD!
Narrator:
...RISKING THEIR LIVES
ON THE HUNT FOR GOLD
IN THE RAGING WATERS
OF MCKINLEY CREEK,
ONE OF THE WORLD'S
MOST DANGEROUS MINE SITES.
I'D LOVE TO PULL UP ABOUT
A BUCKET OF GOLD,
JUST A BIG,
BIG BUCKET OF GOLD.
THAT WOULD MAKE MY YEAR.
THAT WOULD MAKE MY 10 YEARS.
Narrator: FIVE THOUSAND FEET UP
IN THE CHILKAT MOUNTAINS,
A SERIES OF GLACIERS
ERODED GOLD
FROM THE MOTHER LODE
OVER MILLIONS OF YEARS.
MELTWATER CARRIED IT DOWNSTREAM
AND DEPOSITED POCKETS OF GOLD
IN THE BENDS
AND PLUNGE POOLS
OF THESE REMOTE, RUGGED CREEKS.
A HUNDRED YEARS AGO, OLD-TIMERS
HAULED NEARLY
80,000 OUNCES OF GOLD
FROM THESE CREEKS
WORTH TODAY ALMOST $100 MILLION.
THE OLD-TIME MINERS COULDN'T
GET TO WHERE I'M DIGGING NOW.
IT'S JUST TOO DAMN HARD.
THIS YEAR, I'VE GOT MORE
EQUIPMENT AND MORE PEOPLE.
WE'RE DEFINITELY GOING TO GET
DOWN TO THE JACKPOT.
WE'RE THE ONLY REDNECKS
CRAZY ENOUGH TO DO THIS [BLEEP],
AND WE'RE BACK AGAIN.
WHOO-HOO!
Narrator: WES RICHARDSON
AND HIS BROTHER, PAUL,
[ WES TARZAN YELLS ]
HAVE RETURNED FROM TEXAS
FOR THEIR SHARE
OF THE MCKINLEY FORTUNE.
YOU KNOW, WE'RE ALL A BIT CRAZY,
AND WE'VE GOT THAT FEVER.
I'M READY TO FIND THE GOLD.
IT'S TIME TO GET THE GOLD!
Carlos:
LET'S ROCK AND ROLL, BROTHER!
OH, YEAH!
WHOO-HOO!
BACK TO WORK!
Narrator: EX-US MARINE AND DIVER
CARLOS MINOR...
MORNING COMMUTE, MAN!
WHOO!
Narrator: ...HAS EVEN MORE
AT STAKE THIS SEASON.
I JUST HAD A KID, JUST HAD
A LITTLE GIRL, LITTLE GIRL.
THE DEAL WAS WITH MY WIFE
WAS FOR ME TO COME UP
IN THE FIRST SEASON.
WE COULD HAVE A KID,
AND WE'LL GET A CHURCH WEDDING.
SO ONE DOWN.
IF WE FIND GOLD, CHURCH WEDDING,
EVERYBODY IS INVITED.
ALL RIGHT.
-YOU READY?
-SEE Y'ALL ON THE OTHER SIDE!
-LET'S DO IT.
-HERE WE GO!
Fred: AH, HERE COMES OUR NEW
GUY, RICH.
HE'S IN FROM OREGON.
Man: DON'T LOOK DOWN!
OH.
Fred:
HE RUNS A COMPUTER BUSINESS,
BUT HE IS REALLY HANDY
WITH A WRENCH.
OH, MY [BLEEP].
WHAT AM I DOING?
I NEED THAT.
HE'S LEFT HIS FAMILY.
[BLEEP] [BLEEP].
Rich: THAT WAS CRAZY.
I WAS SCARED TO DEATH
WHEN I TOOK OFF,
AND I'M SHAKING RIGHT NOW.
OH, MY [BLEEP].
THAT WAS CRAZY.
Carlos:
NOW THE REAL WORK STARTS.
NOW WE STILL GOT TO HIKE
TO THE [BLEEP] DANG MINE SITE.
COME ON, GUYS.
I KNOW THERE'S GOLD ON MY CLAIM.
I'M A GET IT THIS SEASON.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
EVERYBODY, WATCH OUT!
Narrator:
TO GET TO THE MINE SITE,
THEY HAVE A MILE-AND-A-HALF HIKE
THROUGH REMOTE
ALASKAN WILDERNESS.
Man: I KNOW I HEAR SOMETHING
COME FROM UP THAT WAY.
-AH!
-BEAR!
-BEAR! HEY!
-THERE'S A BEAR!
-YAH!
-RIGHT THERE!
-HYAH, HYAH, HYAH!
-GET OUT OF HERE!
-BEAR!
-YAH!
-HE'S ALL RIGHT. HE'S GONE.
Carlos:
WHOA, THAT WAS CLOSE.
Man:YOU KNOW THEY'RE HUNGRY
RIGHT NOW.
-YEAH.
-REALLY HUNGRY.
-HERE WE GO.
Narrator: THE NEXT CHALLENGE:
A 300-FOOT DESCENT
TO THE RAGING CREEK BELOW.
RICH, I KNOW YOU'RE NEW,
SO JUST DON'T DIE.
ALL RIGHT?
THIS IS DANGEROUS STUFF HERE.
-GOT YOU.
IF YOU KNOCK A ROCK LOOSE,
YELL, "ROCK."
OKAY.
ROCKS!
Narrator: THESE TREACHEROUS
RAVINES ARE THE REASON NO ONE
HAS YET MINED THE GOLD
FROM DUSTIN'S CLAIM.
-WHOA!
-OH!
-WHOA.
-OH [BLEEP]!
-FRED!
I'M ALL RIGHT.
-WHOA.
-HOLY MOLY, THAT WAS CLOSE!
HELL, THIS IS WHERE I WANTED
TO GO IN THE FIRST PLACE.
WATCHING FRED WALK THIS HILL,
HE'S ALMOST 75 NOW,
AND I'M JUST STARTING TO WONDER
HOW LONG HE CAN DO THIS STUFF,
SO HOPEFULLY THIS YEAR
IS OUR YEAR TO HIT IT BIG.
I'M $75,000 IN DEBT,
AND IF I DON'T GET DOWN THERE
IN THE GOLD, I'M SCREWED.
THE SOONER WE CAN GET STARTED,
THE BETTER.
HOLY [BLEEP].
BRIDGE IS DOWN!
Carlos:
OH, THAT DON'T LOOK GOOD.
Man: WHAT THE HELL?
-AW, IT SPLIT IN HALF, MAN!
-WHOA!
-YEAH.
-THEY GOT OUR BRIDGE.
WELL, WE GOT A LITTLE BUMP
IN THE ROAD,
BUT HELL, THAT AIN'T
GOING TO STOP US.
THAT IS NOTHING.
IT LOST A FEW BOARDS,
BUT WE COULD PROBABLY BOLT
THAT THING ALL THE WAY THROUGH.
THIS IS GOING TO BE A BUNCH
OF WORK, BUT WE CAN DO IT,
AND WE'RE GOING TO GET DOWN
AND GET THE GOLD.
-AMEN, BROTHER!
-RIGHT ON.
-AMEN!
-YEP.
LAST SEASON, HOW MUCH GOLD
DID YOU GUYS GET?
-WE GOT A COUPLE OUNCES.
-YEAH.
I MEAN, WHY WOULD YOU WANT TO
COME BACK TO THIS PLACE,
I MEAN, THE EXACT SAME SPOT
WHEN YOU GOT VERY LITTLE GOLD?
WE'RE HERE BECAUSE WE KNOW
THERE'S GOLD DOWN THERE.
I'VE SEEN GOLD 15 FEET DOWN
IN THAT HOLE
RIGHT UNDERNEATH THAT BRIDGE
AND A LITTLE BIT BACK.
SOON AS WE GOT TO THE BOTTOM
OF THIS HOLE,
WE STARTED FINDING
GOLD IMMEDIATELY.
LIKE, IT JUST STARTED HAPPENING
JUST IMMEDIATELY.
Narrator: LAST SEASON...
LOOK AT THAT RIGHT THERE!
...AFTER 20 WEEKS
OF DREDGING...
WOW.
...THE DAKOTA BOYS
HIT A PAY STREAK
THAT PRODUCED HALF THEIR SEASON
TOTAL IN JUST 2 DAYS.
-THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
-WHOA!
-CLEAN THAT SUCKER OUT!
-WHOO!
Narrator:
BUT JUST AS THEY STARTED TO HIT
THIS MAJOR DEPOSIT...
GET HIM OUT OF THERE!
WHOO, DOGGY!
LOOK AT THAT MOTHER[BLEEP].
...A FEROCIOUS STORM...
THAT BRIDGE IS GOING TO GO!
Man: GET OUT!
GET OUT!
...FORCED THEM TO LEAVE BEHIND
A TREASURE CHEST...
Man: WATCH OUT!
...THAT COULD CONTAIN
MILLIONS IN GOLD.
♪♪
THE GOLD IS IN THAT HOLE,
AND I'M GOING TO TELL YOU WHAT.
WE'RE GOING TO GET IT THIS YEAR.
Man: YOU GOT TO
HAVE TRUST IN US, MAN.
-IT'S THERE, BRO.
-WE'VE DONE THE TESTING.
Man: IT'S THERE, MAN.
Wes: MOTHER NATURE
KICKED OUR ASS LAST SEASON
BUT NOT THIS SEASON.
THAT'S MY DAUGHTER'S FRICKING
COLLEGE EDUCATION RIGHT THERE.
THAT'S MY NEW HOME.
I'M ITCHING TO GET IN THIS
[BLEEP] DAMN WATER.
TO DIVE IN THIS WATER,
YOU DEFINITELY HAVE GOT TO BE
A LITTLE BIT OF CRAZY,
A LOT OF GUTS
AND SOME BIG BRASS BALLS.
-I THINK WE OUGHT TO GET ON IT.
-LET'S GO.
-WHOO!
Fred:
I'M GOING TO HIT 75 THIS SUMMER.
THIS IS GOING TO BE MY SUMMER.
WE'RE GOING TO GET SOME GOLD.
Narrator: UP AHEAD...
WELCOME TO THE DEATH ZONE.
YEAH, DUDE!
THE HARDEST PART IS THIS WATER
WANTS TO EAT US.
-I SEE A HELICOPTER.
-HERE WE GO!
NO, NO!
OH, [BLEEP]!
Man: PULL THE ROCK, MAN!
Fred: IT AIN'T LONG ENOUGH.
HEY, NOT LONG ENOUGH!
OH [BLEEP]!
WE GOT TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO GET ACROSS HERE.
THAT'S THE BIGGEST PROBLEM.
Narrator:
HIGH IN THE CHILKAT MOUNTAINS,
THE DAKOTA BOYS RETURN
TO THEIR MINE SITE.
Dustin: WE CAN MAKE
A WORKSTATION OFF OF THAT.
Man: YEAH.
IT LOOKS
PRETTY DANGEROUS TO ME.
Narrator: THEY CAN'T DIVE
FOR GOLD UNTIL THEY REPAIR
THE WINTER STORM DAMAGE.
TO FIX THIS BRIDGE,
I NEED TO GET THE LINE
ACROSS WHERE IT HANGS DOWN,
AND WE CAN WORK OFF OF THAT
AND JACK UP THAT OTHER SIDE.
WE'RE GOING TO USE THIS LINE
AS A FRICKING ANCHOR TO...
TO PICK UP ON IT
WITH COME-ALONGS
AND THEN BOLT IT TOGETHER.
Narrator: DUSTIN'S PLAN --
USE THE EXISTING CABLE
ACROSS THE CREEK
TO ATTACH A LINE TO A RATCHET,
THEN HOIST THE BRIDGE UP
SO IT'S LEVEL.
NEXT, PULL THE SHORT BROKEN END
OF THE BEAM BACK INTO PLACE
AND SECURE THE REPAIR
WITH FOUR WOODEN BRACES.
WELCOME TO THE DEATH ZONE.
THIS IS VERY EXTREME.
WHOO.
Carlos:
TAKE YOUR TIME, BROTHER.
ALL RIGHT.
[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
UGLIEST KNOT I EVER DID TIE.
WELL, I SET MY LINE, AND I THINK
I'M ZIP-LINING BACK DOWN.
[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
A-FRICKING-MAZING, MAN.
Narrator:
TO ATTACH DUSTIN'S ROPE,
SOMEONE NEEDS TO CROSS
THE BROKEN BRIDGE.
PAUL IS FIRST TO VOLUNTEER.
-PAUL!
-NO MISTAKES!
IF YOU FALL IN THAT WATER,
YOU'RE [BLEEP], MAN.
THAT CURRENT AIN'T NO JOKE.
IT'LL SPIN AROUND AND JUST BITE
[BLEEP] OUT OF YOU.
♪♪
WHOO!
-IS THIS YOU?
-YEAH!
-RIGHT HERE, RIGHT?
-YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
Narrator:
NEXT, CARLOS MUST ATTACH THE
RATCHET LINE TO THE BRIDGE
JUST INCHES ABOVE THE DEADLY
38-DEGREE MELTWATER.
CAN YOU SEE WHAT'S BELOW ME?
AND I'M RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE,
BROTHER.
LOOK AT ME,
[BLEEP] GETTING READY TO DIE.
Dustin:
THAT'S A REALLY BAD SPOT
TO FALL, SO DON'T FALL.
LIFT UP ON THAT THING.
CAN YOU LIFT ON IT?
♪♪
-AH!
-AH! [BLEEP] YEAH!
Narrator:
IT'S DOWN TO CARLOS TO MANEUVER
THE 300-POUND BROKEN SECTION
OF BEAM BACK INTO PLACE.
OPA!
SON OF A [BLEEP].
[BLEEP] RIVER, MAN.
Carlos: OH! WHOA!
-OH!
-[BLEEP] [BLEEP].
I GOT YOU.
I GOT YOU, GOT YOU, GOT YOU.
HEY, HOLD IT. HOLD ON. PULL IT!
PULL IT! PULL IT! PULL IT!
I'M CAUGHT.
-GOT YOU?
-YEAH.
-DON'T GET IN THE PINCH POINT.
GET OUT OF THERE!
-GOT IT.
THANK YOU!
ALL RIGHT.
HOLD ON.
THAT WAS BAD.
LET'S NOT DO THAT AGAIN.
THE HARDEST PART IS THIS WATER
WANTS TO EAT US.
GUYS, WE GOT TO FIX THIS BRIDGE.
COME ON, GUYS.
Carlos: COME ON, MAN.
YOU GOT IT!
NOW WE MIGHT BE ABLE
TO LIFT THAT UP.
HERE WE GO, MAN!
COMING UP.
YEAH, YEAH.
THIS IS GOING TO WORK.
ALL RIGHT.
I NEED THIS BOARD TO BE
JACKED UP WHEN I LIFT THIS.
Carlos: OKAY.
COME ON, GUYS.
COME ON, MAN.
YOU GOT IT!
-[ GRUNTS ]
-THAT'S IT! THAT'S IT, MAN!
-THAT'S THE RIGHT...
WHY DON'T WE PUT
A TOURNIQUET ON IT?
GOT IT.
-CARLOS TIES A ROPE TOURNIQUET
TO PULL THE TWO PARTS
OF THE BEAM TOGETHER.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO TWIST THAT WITH?
A PIPE OR SOMETHING.
YEAH, DUDE!
THAT'LL HOLD IT.
Dustin: GOING TO BRACE IT UP
WITH SOME BOARDS.
WE'RE GOING TO PUT SOME BOARDS
ON THE INSIDE AND THE OUTSIDE.
-THAT SHOULD BE IT, HUH?
-I THINK THAT'LL DO US.
AH!
TWO MORE BOARDS,
WE'LL BE DONE!
THAT'S IT!
ALL RIGHT!
WELL, WE GOT IT DONE.
-GOOD JOB, GUYS.
-GOOD JOB, MAN.
HELL YEAH!
WE PUT IT RIGHT BACK TOGETHER
WITH BUBBLE GUM AND DUCT TAPE,
BUT IT'S TOGETHER, AND IT'S
CROSSABLE, SO THAT'S A BRIDGE.
I MEAN, THE REAL WORLD,
THIS IS A PIECE OF TRASH,
BUT [BLEEP]
THIS IS BEAUTIFUL HERE, MAN.
Narrator:
NEXT DAY, DOWN AT THEIR
BASE CAMP ON PORCUPINE CREEK...
-SO DUCT TAPE IT.
-ALL RIGHT.
-THAT SOUNDS...
-IT'LL GET US BY.
Narrator:
...FRED AND NEW GUY
RICH ARE REASSEMBLING
THE DREDGE THEY USED
LAST SEASON.
THIS IS THE OLD DREDGE THAT
WE WERE USING, NICE AND COMPACT.
BASICALLY, ALL THIS THING IS IS
A GIANT WATER VACUUM CLEANER.
Narrator:
THIS SEASON, DUSTIN HAS
A SECRET WEAPON...
OH, GET OUT OF TOWN, DUDE!
...A BRAND-NEW $17,000 DREDGE
CAPABLE OF PROCESSING
12 YARDS OF PAY DIRT AN HOUR,
TWICE AS MUCH AS FRED'S OLD ONE.
Carlos: THIS FRICKING SLUICE
IS FRICKING HUGE, MAN!
FROM POINT A TO POINT B,
IT HAS ITS OWN ZIP CODE.
NO GOLD IS EVER GOING
TO ESCAPE THIS.
NO.
HOW MUCH DIRT ARE WE GOING
TO MOVE WITH [BLEEP]?
I'M HOPING AT LEAST
TWICE AS MUCH.
-GAH!
-THE DREDGE IS...
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
IT'S ABOUT...
-GOD.
...THREE TIMES THE SIZE,
SURFACE SIZE.
THIS FIXES ALL OUR PROBLEMS.
WHAT THE HELL YOU GOT
OVER HERE ANYWAY?
Dustin:
A GIANT-SIZED DREDGE.
YEP.
STEP IT RIGHT IN.
OUR SLUICE BOX IS JUST ABOUT THE
SAME SIZE AS YOUR FULL DREDGE.
BIGGER ISN'T NECESSARILY BETTER.
Dustin:
FRED WON'T ADMIT IT,
BUT HE WANTS TO WORK
OFF OF THIS MACHINE.
HE'S LOOKING AT HIS LITTLE,
BITTY TOY OVER THERE,
AND HE'S FEELING
A LITTLE INADEQUATE.
THERE IT IS.
AND WE'RE READY TO GO.
IT'S GOING TO MAKE ME
SOME GOLD NOW.
ALL WE GOT TO DO IS GET
IT UP THERE AND GET STARTED.
Narrator:
WITH TWO DREDGES THIS SEASON,
FATHER AND SON
WILL BE WORKING
TOGETHER SIDE BY SIDE.
THESE ARE DUSTIN'S CLAIMS.
TECHNICALLY, I'M WORKING FOR HIM
BUT BASICALLY AS A...
MAYBE I'LL BE AN OLD SAGE,
AN ADVISOR OR SOMETHING
OF THAT NATURE.
Dustin: A LITTLE BIT
OF LUMBER COMING.
Wes: EVENTUALLY,
WE'RE GOING TO NEED IT.
FRED, THAT'S NOT JUST
A LITTLE BIT OF LUMBER, MAN.
WE ALREADY TALKED ABOUT THIS,
THAT I DIDN'T WANT YOU BUILDING
A WHOLE BUNCH OF STUFF.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
-I JUST SAID...
NO, NO.
I'M NOT...
SO IF YOU NEED PIECES OF LUMBER,
HOW DO YOU GET THEM
OUT THERE...
-WHAT DO I NEED...
-...CARRY THEM?
-...LUMBER FOR, FRED?
THERE'S NOTHING ON THE OTHER
SIDE OF THE CREEK
TO EVEN WALK ON.
EVERYTHING IS...
-WE'RE NOT BUILDING...
-...LIKE THIS.
-...THIS YEAR.
WE'RE NOT BUILDING.
HOW ABOUT IF I JUST LEAVE ALL OF
THAT SITTING RIGHT THERE,
AND YOU PAY
THE HELICOPTER BILL
WHEN WE HAVE TO HAVE IT
OUT THERE?
WATCH YOURSELF DOWN THERE.
WELL, I'M JUST PLANNING AHEAD.
Dustin: FRED IS GOING TO DECK
THE ENTIRE CREEK IF I LET HIM,
AND WE'RE NOT BUILDING
A WHOLE BUNCH OF STUFF.
IT'S NOT HAPPENING THIS YEAR,
AND WE'VE HAD THESE DISCUSSIONS,
AND HE DECIDED
HE WAS GOING TO GO AHEAD
AND BUY THE LUMBER ANYWAY.
OKAY.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
HE'S GOT NO RIGHT TO DO
ANY OF THIS STUFF.
YES, SIR.
YOU TOO.
HE DON'T OWN ANYTHING.
HIS NAME IS ON NOTHING.
IT'S JUST, SOMEHOW,
HE THINKS HE'S IN CHARGE,
AND THIS IS WHERE WE GET INTO
TROUBLE, BUT I'M IN CONTROL.
IT'S NOT GOING UP THERE.
♪♪
SO TODAY WE'VE GOT A HELICOPTER
COMING SO WE CAN...
WE'RE GOING TO LIFT ALL OF
OUR STUFF INTO THE DIVE SITE.
I SPENT EVERY DIME
I COULD ON THIS STUFF,
AND I'M JUST WORRIED THAT THE
HELICOPTER LIFT MAY GO WRONG,
AND MY DREDGE
MIGHT GET DESTROYED,
AND THAT'LL BE THE END
OF EVERYTHING HERE
BECAUSE I CAN'T BUY ANOTHER ONE.
I JUST NEED IT TO GO OKAY.
WHO KNOWS?
HOPEFULLY, FRED DOESN'T
MESS THIS UP FOR ME.
♪♪
I'LL TAKE THESE THINGS OFF
SO THEY DON'T GET
HUNG UP ON ANYTHING.
WE WOULD BE IN SOME SERIOUS
TROUBLE IF WE SMASH THIS.
YOU BETTER NOT SMASH IT.
THIS IS OUR $17,000 DREDGE.
YOU DROP THIS THING OUT OF THE
SKY, AND WE'RE JUST GOING HOME.
OH, LORD. BIG DAY.
WE GOT HELICOPTER FLIGHTS TODAY.
WE'VE GOT PROBABLY ABOUT A HALF
A DOZEN OR SO LOADS
TO HAUL OUT OF HERE.
WE GOT TWO DREDGES.
WE GOT FUEL TO TAKE OUT THERE.
WE HAVE BASKETS.
WE HAVE MATERIALS.
WES, DON'T LET HIM
BRING UP THAT LUMBER, MAN.
WE DON'T NEED IT UP THERE.
PLEASE.
-OKAY. I'LL DO MY BEST.
THE LUMBER NEEDS
TO STAY DOWN HERE.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY SPACE
FOR IT UP THERE.
Wes: ALL RIGHT.
SEE Y'ALL IN A FEW.
Narrator:
DUSTIN, CARLOS, AND PAUL
HEAD TO THE DIVE SITE,
LEAVING FRED
IN CHARGE OF LOADING.
♪♪
Fred: IT'S MARY!
HOW YOU DOING?
HEY, FRED.
HOW'S IT GOING?
LONG TIME, NO SEE.
-THAT'S IT!
IT'S BEEN ABOUT A YEAR
OR TWO AT LEAST...
-YEAH, NO KIDDING.
-...SINCE THE LAST TIME.
WE HAVE PROBABLY A HALF
A DOZEN DIFFERENT THINGS.
-OKAY.
-WE'VE GOT THAT DREDGE.
-WE HAVE A BIG ONE OVER HERE.
OH, OKAY.
THAT PARTICULAR UNIT IS GOING
TO LAND IN THE WATER,
AND DUSTIN WILL DIRECT YOU WHERE
HE WANTS TO LAND THAT THING.
YOU GUYS HAVE TAG LINES ON THAT
SO THE GUYS CAN...
THERE'S GOING TO BE A TAG LINE
ON IT TO GRAB IT.
-YES.
-YOU HAVE NETS?
I DO HAVE NETS.
I BROUGHT TWO NETS.
OKAY, TWO NETS, GREAT.
Mary: I LIKE SLINGING
BECAUSE I LIKE THE CHALLENGE,
BUT IT DOES REQUIRE
PRACTICE AND PATIENCE.
GOOD, GOOD, GOOD.
THERE'S OUR FIRST LIFT.
-THERE YOU GO!
-ALL RIGHT.
Fred: CLEAR!
WHOO-WEE!
GOOD, SMOOTH LIFT.
THAT IS BADASS.
Narrator:
THE ONLY WAY TO GET EQUIPMENT
TO THE REMOTE MINE SITE
IS A 2-MILE FLIGHT
THROUGH NARROW MOUNTAIN CANYONS.
Man: HERE WE GO!
WHOO-HOO!
Man: THINGS ARE
GETTING REAL, BROTHER!
Mary:
DUSTIN, I GOT ONE MORE NET LOAD
FIRST AND THEN THE DREDGES.
Dustin: COPY THAT.
ON THE WAY!
OVER THERE!
YEAH!
WATCH YOURSELF!
-I GOT IT!
-YEP.
-OH, THAT WENT BEAUTIFULLY.
-THAT WAS A GOOD LIFT.
Man:
THAT WAS PERFECT!
Dustin:
JUST ABOUT EVERYTHING IS HERE.
NOW IT'S TIME
TO GET THE DREDGES.
ALL RIGHTY THERE, MARY,
LITTLE DREDGE NEXT.
[ Over radio ]
COPY THAT.
Narrator: NEXT UP --
FRED'S LIGHTWEIGHT DREDGE.
Dustin: YEAH, GO, BABY, GO!
-FLY, BABY, FLY!
-WHOO!
RIGHT NOW, OF COURSE,
THE DREDGES
ARE OUR MOST IMPORTANT ITEMS.
-HERE SHE COMES.
-ALL RIGHT!
GO, GO, GO, GO, GO!
GO, GO, GO!
Narrator:
THE TAG LINE ON THE DREDGE
ALLOWS
DUSTIN TO GUIDE IT
INTO THE LANDING ZONE.
Dustin: AND I'M GOING TO TRY TO
PUT IT RIGHT THERE.
TO YOU.
LITTLE SLACK.
Man: PERFECT!
Fred: [ Over radio ]
THE EAGLE HAS LANDED.
YES.
-THAT'S PERFECT, MAN!
ALL RIGHT, GUYS!
PARKER TIME!
Man: BIG DREDGE NEXT!
Fred: BACK UP A LITTLE BIT.
BACK UP A LITTLE BIT.
MOVE IT FORWARD!
Narrator:
DUSTIN'S NEW DREDGE WEIGHS
1,800 POUNDS.
LOOSEN IT UP.
HE HAS NO CHOICE
BUT TO LAND IT DIRECTLY
IN THE RAGING WATER OF THE CREEK
BECAUSE IT IS TOO HEAVY
TO LIFT BY HAND.
IDEALLY, I WANT IT RIGHT
THERE AGAINST THAT WALL.
I'M A LITTLE NERVOUS.
I AIN'T GOING TO LIE.
YEP!
THAT LOOKS GOOD!
Fred: ALL RIGHT!
LET'S GO.
WHOO, COME ON!
WHERE'S YOUR TAG LINE?
Wes:
THEY DIDN'T WANT A TAG LINE.
THEY WANT TO HOOK IT UP.
I WANTED TO PUT A TAG LINE.
THEY DIDN'T...
WHERE THE HELL IS THE TAG LINE?
THEY DIDN'T WANT ME
TO PUT A TAG LINE.
BULL[BLEEP].
THAT'S THE WRONG THING TO DO.
THEY'VE GOT SOMETHING
OF THEIR OWN PLANNED.
SO HOW ARE THEY GOING TO
HOOK UP A THING
OUT THE MIDDLE OF THE WATER?
-I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK THEY HAD PLANNED
TO HAVE THEIR ROPES
TIED OFF ON THE SIDES,
AND AS SOON AS IT SAT DOWN,
THEY WERE GOING TO GO OVER THERE
AND JUST CLIP IT
WITH CARABINERS.
WELL, THAT'S THE WRONG
THING TO DO.
THAT'S THE WRONG THING TO DO.
Dustin:
YEAH, MARY, I'M GOING TO ASK YOU
TO DO SOMETHING
A LITTLE DIFFERENT
THAN WE PLANNED.
I'M STANDING OVER ON LAND
WITH TWO LINES,
AND I'M GOING TO HOOK INTO IT
UPSTREAM ACROSS THE CREEK.
Mary:
COPY THAT.
I WILL HOLD IT WHILE YOU
ATTACH A LINE
AND THEN SET IT
UPSTREAM FROM YOU.
THAT'S CORRECT.
Narrator:
WHEN THE DREDGE ARRIVES,
DUSTIN WILL ATTACH
TWO TAG LINES.
THE LINES ARE ANCHORED
TO PULLEYS
ON OPPOSITE SIDES OF THE CREEK
TO PREVENT THE RAGING CURRENT
FROM RIPPING THE $17,000
DREDGE DOWNSTREAM.
WE'VE NEVER LANDED A DREDGE
IN THE WATER OUT THERE BEFORE.
THERE'S ALL KINDS OF THINGS
THAT COULD GO WRONG.
PAUL, I NEED YOU BACK
OVER HERE NOW, NOW!
GO OVER HERE!
Narrator: PAUL AND CARLOS
STAND BY WITH THE ANCHORS.
DUSTIN'S CHALLENGE:
CLIP BOTH LINES
ONTO THE HOVERING DREDGE.
♪♪
PAUL!
-COME ON! I GOT IT!
-[BLEEP]
-I GOT IT!
-WHAT THE [BLEEP] HAPPENED?
I MISSED MY CLIP.
TIGHTEN UP!
GO, GO, GO!
-NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
NO, NO, NO!
OH, [BLEEP].
♪♪
THIS IS CRAZY.
Narrator:
DUSTIN HURT'S BRAND-NEW $17,000
DREDGE IS HANGING DANGEROUSLY
ABOVE THE RAGING WATERS
OF MCKINLEY CREEK.
PAUL!
COME ON!
Paul: I GOT [BLEEP].
I GOT IT!
WHAT THE [BLEEP] HAPPENED?
[ BLEEP ].
I MISSED MY CLIP.
TIGHTEN UP!
GO, GO, GO!
-NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
NO, NO, NO!
OH, [BLEEP]!
NO, NO, NO, NO!
Man: AH!
COME ON, DUSTIN!
EASY!
YEAH! HELL YEAH!
WE'RE GOOD!
-OKAY.
THANK YOU.
DROP IT, PLEASE.
Mary: COPY THAT.
THAT WAS ABSOLUTELY PERFECT.
THANK YOU.
THANKS, GUYS.
-YEAH!
-[BLEEP] YEAH!
-WE DID THAT [BLEEP].
-WHOO!
HELL YEAH!
COME ON!
WHAT A [BLEEP] RUSH!
WHOO.
Dustin:
SO DID YOU SEE WHAT HAPPENED?
WHEN I CLIPPED, IT MISSED
AND WENT INTO THE WATER,
AND I WAS LIKE, "OH, NO.
THERE'S ONLY ONE ROPE
ON THIS THING,
AND AND I'VE LOST
MY FRICKING MIND.
SEVENTEEN THOUSAND DOLLARS
IS GOING TO WASH DOWN
THE DAMN CREEK."
OH, MY GOD.
PAUL HAD TO TAKE UP
ALL THE SLACK.
OTHERWISE, THE DREDGE
WOULD'VE TAKEN OFF
BECAUSE I MISSED
THAT LITTLE THING.
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT A STRESSFUL SITUATION.
♪♪
-HANG ON.
-GOT ANOTHER LOAD.
WHAT IS IT?
-YOU SEE IT, PAUL?
-IT'S THE LUMBER.
-AH!
-HE SENT THE LUMBER!
Carlos:
THE LUMBER, BROTHER!
[BLEEP], MAN.
[ LAUGHS ]
Dustin: [BLEEP] DAMN IT.
FRED GOT HIS DAMN WAY.
[ LAUGHS ]
AH, LEAVE IT TO FRED,
BROTHER. LEAVE IT TO FRED.
-UNBELIEVABLE.
-AH, THAT'S FUNNY, MAN.
DUSTIN...
...DID YOU GET
MY SPECIAL DELIVERY UP THERE?
YEAH, WE DROPPED IT
IN THE RIVER.
IT SHOULD BE ABOUT TO YOU
RIGHT NOW IF YOU GO CHECK OUT...
...PORCUPINE CREEK.
[ LAUGHS ]
[ BEEP ]
Narrator:
NEXT DAY, THE DAKOTA BOYS
RETURN TO THE MINE SITE
TO PREPARE FOR
THEIR FIRST DIVE.
Carlos: THINGS ARE COMING
TOGETHER RIGHT NOW,
GOT OUR DREDGE
IN THE WATER.
I'D WANT TO [BLEEP] DIVE, DUDE.
[BLEEP] DANG.
I CAN'T WAIT TO GET BACK
IN THE WATER.
I'M SERIOUS.
-LOOK AT THIS, HUH? LOOK AT IT!
-YEP.
Paul:
IT'S NEVER BEEN THIS CLEAR.
THAT IS THE BEST THAT'S EVER
GOING TO LOOK RIGHT THERE.
Dustin: MAKE NO MISTAKE,
I AM IN A HURRY,
BUT THAT IS THE ONE ROCK,
I THINK, THAT IS DANGEROUS.
GOT TO MOVE THE DEATH ROCK
BEFORE WE GET IN THE WATER.
WE'RE GOING TO PUT
THIS WINCH UP HERE
BECAUSE WE'RE GOING
TO MOVE A ROCK.
HOLD ON.
-ALL RIGHT.
-JUST HOLD ON.
THE KILLER ROCK DOWN THERE,
THE SECOND ONE FROM THE WALL,
IF THE CURRENT COMES UP
WHILE YOU'RE DOWN IN THE HOLE
AND WE LEAVE IT THERE
AND IT MOVES JUST A LITTLE BIT
AND DECIDES TO JUST ROLL
INTO THE HOLE
WHERE YOU'RE AT, YOU'RE DEAD.
YOU'LL NEVER KNOW YOU WERE DEAD.
Narrator:
DUSTIN'S PLAN -- DRILL ANCHOR
BOLTS INTO THE 3-TON BOULDER
AND ATTACH A LINE
SO THEY CAN WINCH
THE KILLER ROCK
SAFELY OUT OF THEIR DIVE SITE.
WHOO!
MY ASS IS FREEZING, MAN!
FRICKING AMAZING, MAN.
WHOO-HOO!
AND YOU THOUGHT YOUR JOB
WAS HARD!
WHO THINKS ABOUT DOING
STUPID STUFF LIKE THIS?
NOBODY THINKS ABOUT
STUPID STUFF LIKE THIS!
♪♪
WHOO, WHOO!
THAT'S COLD!
[ GROWLS ]
AH!
READY?
YEAH!
PULL THE ROCK, MAN!
LET ME LOOK AT IT
BEFORE YOU PULL IT!
-HOLD ON!
-WAIT A MINUTE!
HOLD ON!
THE INSPECTOR IS HERE!
DAMN RIGHT!
ALL I COULD SEE
WAS SOMEBODY DRIVING
A BOLT 2 INCHES INTO THE ROCK.
IT AIN'T LONG ENOUGH.
Dustin:
HEY, JUST SMILE AND SAY,
"HEY, LOOK HOW [BLEEP]
GOOD THAT LOOKS."
Fred: NOT LONG ENOUGH!
NOT LONG [BLEEP]
ENOUGH, THAT LONG!
Dustin: DOESN'T MATTER!
WE'VE DONE THIS BEFORE.
Fred: I JUST SAW HIM PUT IN A
SHORT ANCHOR BOLT THERE,
BUT WHAT WE REALLY NEED
IS ABOUT A 12-INCH-LONG ANCHOR
INSTEAD OF ABOUT A COUPLE
OF 8-INCH ONES,
MAKES A BIG DIFFERENCE
ON THE STRENGTH OF THOSE BOLTS.
WELL, FRED'S GOT HIS IDEAS,
AND I'VE GOT MINE.
WHEN IT COMES DOWN TO IT,
I'M IN CHARGE.
GO AHEAD AND PULL IT?
GO!
COME ON, BABY!
YOU CAN DO IT!
-COME ON, ROLL.
-YEAH! LOOK.
IT'S GOING TO SPIN.
-ROLL!
-DID IT MOVE?
-YEAH.
Dustin: HELL YEAH!
-KEEP GOING.
-COME ON.
A LITTLE BIT MORE.
-OH, [BLEEP].
-WHAT BROKE?
THE ANCHOR BOLT BUSTED.
-IT CAME OUT, HUH?
-YEP.
[ LAUGHS ] JUST PULLED THE DAMN
THING OUT OF THE ROCK.
HOLLERED AT THEM EARLIER,
BUT THERE AGAIN
THE YOUNG ONES DON'T LISTEN.
CHECK IT OUT, MAN.
THOSE ARE THE BOLTS
THAT BLEW OUT, MAN.
OH, GOOD [BLEEP].
YEAH.
I'VE USED THAT BEFORE,
AND IT'S BEEN JUST FINE,
BUT NOW IT'S TIME
TO STEP IT UP.
LOOK WHAT I GOT NOW.
THIS IS THE BIGGEST ONES
WE CAN USE FOR THIS SITUATION,
SO IT'S NO COMPARISON.
MAN, IF WE BLOW THOSE OUT,
WE'RE IN SERIOUS TROUBLE.
ROUND TWO!
THIS IS LITERALLY MAN
AGAINST ROCK!
WE'RE GOING TO WAR
WITH EACH OTHER.
HOLY [BLEEP] IS IT COLD.
-THANK YOU, AMIGO!
-YES, SIR.
DO YOU FEEL COMFORTABLE
PUTTING THE CHAIN ON?
-YES, SIR.
-THEN GO.
Narrator:
A WEEK AGO, NEW GUY RICH
WAS REFORMATTING HARD DRIVES
AT HIS COMPUTER STORE
IN OREGON.
-HERE.
-HEY, FRED.
Fred: YOU'RE PUTTING AN
INEXPERIENCED GUY OUT THERE.
YOU'RE [BLEEP] WITH DANGER.
Dustin:
SINK OR SWIM, FRED.
SING OR SWIM LITERALLY.
-THAT'S BULL[BLEEP].
-HE'S A GROWN-ASS MAN.
TREAT HIM LIKE ONE.
UGH.
SEE WHAT I HAVE TO DEAL
WITH EVERY DAY.
Fred:
PUT IT RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE!
PUT IT IN THE MIDDLE
IF YOU CAN.
YEAH.
SLIDE YOUR HOOK IN THE MIDDLE.
THERE YOU GO!
YEAH!
ALL RIGHT.
COME ON OUT OF THERE.
EXCELLENT JOB, RICH.
-YEAH!
-EXCELLENT JOB.
LOOK LIKE THEY GOT THIS THING
SET UP THE RIGHT WAY.
OH, YEAH.
YOU GOT IT.
Dustin: OH, GOOD.
WE GOT FRED'S OKAY.
WE CAN NOW GO ON
WITH OUR LIVES.
FRED HAS GIVEN US THE OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
PULL IT.
Carlos:
COME ON, MAN.
KEEP WINCHING THAT THING
IF IT'LL GO.
COME ON!
PULL!
Fred:
THAT IS A BIG SON OF A [BLEEP].
Paul:
THAT IS A BIG ROCK.
I WANT IT TO ROLL!
SEE WHAT YOU GOT.
MAKE IT SCREAM, BROTHER!
MAKE IT SCREAM!
COME ON, BABY,
A LITTLE BIT MORE!
-COME ON, MAN!
-YOU GOT IT, PAUL!
THERE IT GOES!
WHOO-WEE!
-WELL, IT'S OUT!
-YEAH!
IT'S OUT!
-WHOO!
-GOOD JOB.
-NO MATTER WHAT!
-IT'S TIME TO DIVE, GUYS!
♪♪
HEY, RICH.
I NEED A MILITARY GUY.
YOU KNOW HOW TO FOLD A FLAG?
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME,
ABOUT 18 YEARS.
LET'S SEE. LET'S SEE IF I CAN
REMEMBER HOW TO DO THIS.
IT'S BEEN ABOUT 40 YEARS
SINCE I FOLDED A FLAG UP.
I REMEMBER A MILITARY DETAIL
WHEN MY FATHER GOT KILLED.
MY DAD, WHO WAS EX-MARINE
AND EX-NAVY,
HE DID BOTH SERVICES.
HE GOT KILLED IN 1958.
I WAS ONLY ABOUT 13,
14 YEARS OLD,
AND I REMEMBER THEM
FOLDING THAT FLAG
AND HANDING IT TO MY MOTHER.
OOH.
GOT TO BE PROUD
OF YOUR FLAG, MAN.
ABSOLUTELY.
I'D DIE FOR IT.
I THINK IT'S CLOSE, ESPECIALLY
FOR A COUPLE OF NOVICES.
-IT IS. [ LAUGHS ]
-AMEN.
♪♪
TODAY, WE ARE GOING DIVING.
I'M GOING DIVING.
I KNOW THE WATER IS A LITTLE
OUT OF CONTROL TODAY.
-DANGER.
-HUH?
-DANGER, BOSS.
-IT IS DANGEROUS.
I'VE DONE IT BEFORE,
SO WE'RE DOING IT AGAIN.
IF SOMETHING SHOULD HAPPEN,
I ACCEPT THE RESPONSIBILITY
OF THAT.
SO THERE WE GO.
PAUL, YOU'RE GOING TO BE
ON COMMS.
-ALL RIGHT.
-CARLOS...
GOT YOU.
...YOU'RE GOING TO GET
MY TAG LINE.
ALL RIGHT.
GET HER DONE.
I JUST WANT TO GET IN THIS DAMN
WATER AND FIND MY GOLD.
I WANT MY POCKETS FULL OF GOLD
RIGHT NOW.
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME SINCE I'VE
EVER SEEN ANYTHING LIKE THIS.
Rich: IT'S BRUTAL.
THERE'S ABSOLUTELY NO WAY
WE'D BE DIVING
IN ANY OF THIS STUFF,
TOTALLY OUT OF CONTROL.
Narrator:
FIVE HUNDRED TONS OF ICE-COLD
GLACIAL MELTWATER
POUR THROUGH MCKINLEY
CREEK EVERY MINUTE.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M GOING IN.
I GOT TO PUT ON MY SUPER SUIT.
-DUSTIN.
-YEAH?
I'M JUST TIRED OF BUILDING
AND FIXING AND RIGGING STUFF.
I JUST WANT TO DREDGE.
LET ME GET UNDER THE SURFACE.
IT'LL BE FINE.
START SLOW.
-EH, HE AIN'T GOING TO LISTEN.
HE AIN'T GOING TO LISTEN.
I'M A LITTLE NERVOUS.
THE WATER IS A LITTLE FASTER
THAN I LIKE IT TO BE,
BUT I THINK
I CAN STILL HANDLE IT.
IT'S TIME TO DREDGE
AND GO GET THE DAMN GOLD.
♪♪
Carlos: I KIND OF THINK
THAT DUSTIN IS KIND OF JUMPING
A LITTLE BIT
TOO MUCH RIGHT NOW,
BUT THAT'S WHAT GOLD DOES
FOR YOU, BROTHER.
THAT'S WHAT GOLD DOES.
I GOT YOU.
I'M HERE.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
Dustin: AH!
WHOO-HOO!
HELL YEAH!
-WHOO!
-YEAH!
Man: WHOO!
Narrator: DUSTIN'S NEW DREDGE
IS A FLOATING WASH PLANT.
THE SUCTION HOSE
DRAWS GOLD-BEARING DIRT
UP TO THE ONBOARD SLUICE,
WHICH CATCHES THE HEAVY GOLD
IN ITS RIFFLES.
IT IS ALSO
HIS LIFE-SUPPORT SYSTEM,
PROVIDING AN AIR SUPPLY,
HOT WATER TO HIS DIVE SUIT,
AND A SAFETY LINE TO HAUL HIM
OUT IN CASE OF EMERGENCY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
Fred: MY OPINION, IT'S JUST
UNNECESSARY TO BE GETTING OUT
IN THAT TYPE OF WATER,
A LITTLE BIT OF THAT FATHER
INSTINCT TO KEEP YOUR KID SAFE.
YEAH!
WHOO! [ LAUGHS ]
Man: HELL YEAH.
-AH!
-NOW WE'RE GOING FULL.
-UH-OH.
-OH, [BLEEP]!
-GET HIM! GET HIM! GET HIM!
-GOT HIM! GOT HIM!
GOT HIM.
[ REBREATHER HISSES ]
-DAMN.
-WHOO!
Carlos: I GOT YOU.
Fred:
GETTING UP IN THERE INTO THAT
CURRENT WAS NOT THE THING TO DO.
NAH.
THERE WAS A POINT
WHERE I LIFTED MY HEAD
JUST A LITTLE BIT OF HEAD LIFT,
AND THAT CURRENT JUST WHIPPED ME
BACK, AND I STARTED FLIPPING.
Paul: DUSTIN, FRED!
THERE'S A LITTLE FLAKE
OF GOLD IN THERE!
[ BLEEP ].
THERE'S TWO PIECES OF GOLD
IN THERE THAT YOU CAN SEE!
-ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
-YEAH.
Man: THERE'S QUITE A BIT OF GOLD
RIGHT THERE ACTUALLY.
I LOVE IT!
-WE GOT GOLD, FRED!
-WHOO-HOO!
I GOT TO SEE IT
TO BELIEVE IT.
Dustin: THE SLUICE BOX IS FULL
OF LITTLE BITS OF GOLD.
IT'S INCREDIBLE.
-THAT'S GOLD.
-THAT'S GOLD!
IF FRED SAID IT'S GOLD,
IT'S GOLD.
Man: THAT'S OUR FIRST GOLD
OF THE SEASON.
THAT'S AWESOME, MAN!
I'M NEXT.
THE CURRENT GOT HIM,
BUT DAMNED
IF HE DIDN'T FIND
SOME GOLD ALONG WITH IT.
EXCUSE ME, MAN.
I WANT TO [BLEEP] DIVE, DUDE.
I'M NEXT, MAN.
THIS IS GOING TO HAVE EVERYBODY
READY TO GET IN THE WATER.
WE'RE GOING TO DO
GOOD THIS YEAR.
[ LAUGHS ]
Narrator: THIS SEASON ON
"GOLD RUSH: WHITE WATER"...
Dustin:
THIS IS THE REAL DEAL.
THIS IS DANGEROUS,
AND THIS IS A LOT OF WORK.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
-OH!
-CRAZY [BLEEP] [BLEEP] YOU.
WE'RE GOING TO KICK
A LITTLE ASS.
ARE YOU [BLEEP] KIDDING ME?
Man:
I'M NOT [BLEEP] KIDDING.
Wes:
WE'RE ON THE GOLD ALREADY.
IT'S ONLY GOING TO
GET BETTER FROM HERE.
THE FRICKING WATER
IS KILLER!
Man: THERE IS NO AIR IN THIS
MASK. OH, NEVER MIND.
Fred: SICK AND TIRED
OF THE BULL[BLEEP].
Carlos:
I KNOW A LOT OF DIVERS WHO HAVE
BEEN KILLED 15, 10 FEET OF WATER
BECAUSE THEY GOT TOO COMPLACENT.
-OH, YEAH.
-CAN YOU GUYS PUMP UP
THE HOT WATER
A LITTLE BIT FOR ME, PLEASE?
Man: I'M GOING TO REV UP
THE ENGINES.
-AH, HOT! OH, [BLEEP].
-IS IT TOO HOT?
-TOO HOT! TOO HOT! OW, OW, OW!
-SHUT IT DOWN!
SHUT IT DOWN!
-CARLOS!
-OH, OW, OW!
-GET HIM OUT OF THERE!
-OH, MY [BLEEP].