I HOPE BY THE END OF THIS DAY,
I'LL HAVE FINISHED THE CRACK,
AND I'LL KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT'S DOWN THERE.
♪♪
-DUSTIN?
-YEAH?
THIS IS THE END
OF A VERY LONG CHAPTER.
WHEN YOU GET OLD,
YOU START REALIZING,
YOU LIVE ON MEMORIES.
WELL, I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE
FOR THIS DAY, MAN.
Paul: ROCK! ROCK, ROCK, ROCK,
ROCK, ROCK, ROCK, ROCK.
LOOK OUT.
OH, YEAH. HEY!
WE GOT A LANDSLIDE.
DIVERS UP, DIVERS UP.
WE GOT LANDSLIDE.
-WHOO!
-OH, MY [BLEEP]
Fred: DREDGING IN
THAT CRACK DID THE JOB.
LOOK AT THOSE NUGGETS, DUDE!
--Captions by VITAC--
www.vitac.com
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
DISCOVERY COMMUNICATIONS
♪♪
BY LATE MORNING,
EARLY AFTERNOON,
I WILL BE IN THAT WATER.
YOU BETTER GET
IN THE DAMN WATER, MAN.
IT'S REALLY CLOSE
TO THE END OF THE SEASON.
RIGHT NOW, WE HAVE
A CHANCE TO GET GOLD.
WE NEED TO BE DREDGING
AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE.
YUP.
THAT'S TRUE.
WE WILL GO DIVING,
FOR SURE.
[BLEEP] I WAS HAVING SOME CRAMPS
IN MY LEGS LAST...
Wes: YOU WEREN'T SLEEPING WITH A
PORCUPINE LAST NIGHT, WERE YOU?
OH. I WAS WRASSLING
WITH A PORCUPINE, YEAH.
GET OUT OF MY HEAD,
FRED.
WHAT KIND OF A LIE
YOU WANT TO HEAR?
Y'ALL READY TO GO?
FRED, IT'S STILL
REALLY EARLY RIGHT NOW.
BREWED ANOTHER POT,
SO COMING UP.
IF FRED HURT DRINKS MORE
THAN ONE CUP OF COFFEE,
THE WHOLE WORLD SLOWS DOWN,
AND HE GETS SO ANGRY
THAT EVERYBODY IS NOT MOVING
AS FAST AS HIS BRAIN.
A THE LITTLE BIT OF TRUTH
TO THAT.
TIME TO GET STARTED
THIS MORNING.
TODAY IS A BIG DAY.
WE ARE DOWN TO BEDROCK.
I HAVE NO DOUBT WE'RE GOING
TO FIND SOME GOLD.
WHERE THE HELL IS EVERYBODY?
[ INSECTS CHIRPING ]
EVERYBODY ELSE IS
IN SLOW MOTION.
LET'S GO.
Narrator: HIGH IN ALASKA'S
CHILKAT MOUNTAINS,
THE DAKOTA BOYS ARE SEARCHING
FOR A PILE OF BEDROCK GOLD
THAT WILL CHANGE
THEIR LIVES FOREVER.
Dustin: HOPEFULLY, IT IS ENOUGH
TO PAY FOR THE SEASON
AND MAKE SOME MONEY.
Narrator:
DUSTIN HURT HAS NOW SUNK
OVER $75,000 INTO HIS OPERATION.
HE NEEDS TO REPAY IT ALL
BEFORE WINTER HITS,
OR HIS CREW WON'T GET PAID.
I HAVE A LOT INVESTED.
BROUGHT MY WHOLE FAMILY UP HERE
AND HOPING TO WALK AWAY
WITH HUNDREDS OF OUNCES,
YOU KNOW, GET MY DAUGHTER
A GOOD START IN LIFE.
IF WE DON'T MAKE OUR FORTUNE
THIS YEAR,
IT'S GONNA BE A COLD,
HUNGRY WINTER FOR MY FAMILY.
HEY, HONEY.
HOW YOU BEEN?
MISSED YOU.
LAST WEEK, EVERYBODY
WAS DEPRESSED.
HEADS WERE DOWN.
NOW THAT WE'VE HIT BEDROCK,
YOU CAN SEE HOW CHEERFUL
EVERYBODY IS AGAIN.
EVERYBODY IS HAVING FUN.
EVERYBODY IS SMILING.
WE'RE IN A GOOD SPOT
TO ACTUALLY HIT THE MOTHER LODE.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
FRED AND I ARE GONNA GO DOWN.
SO WHAT WE'RE DOING IS,
WE'LL DIG AND GET ALL THE WAY
UPSTREAM INTO THE CRACK,
ABOUT 8 FEET UP FROM
WHERE WE DUG DOWN TO BEDROCK.
IN THE SIDES OF THE WALLS,
THIS FORMATION IS PERFECT.
IF IT GOES ACROSS THE BOTTOM,
IT COULD BE THE BIGGEST
NUGGET CATCH WE'VE EVER SEEN.
Narrator: DUSTIN'S PLAN --
START ON THE BEDROCK
THEY EXPOSED LAST WEEK.
THEN STRIP MATERIAL
FROM THE UPSTREAM WALL,
DIVING DEEPER THAN EVER
BEFORE TOWARDS THE NUGGET TRAP,
WHICH COULD CONTAIN
MILLIONS IN GOLD.
Dustin: ALL RIGHT.
START IT UP.
Narrator: NOW THEY'RE
JUST 8 FEET DOWNSTREAM
FROM THE NUGGET TRAP.
Dustin: ALL RIGHT.
YOU JUST SHOOT STRAIGHT DOWN
INTO THAT CRACK.
THAT COULD BE FILTHY GOLD RICH,
JUST ABSOLUTELY LIFE-ALTERING.
THAT'S WHY WE DO IT.
Carlos: CAN YOU IMAGINE, MAN,
GETTING READY FOR RETIREMENT?
I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT
BIG HOUSES, BIG CARS.
TO BE THERE FOR MY DAUGHTER,
FOR US, ME AND MY WIFE --
THAT'S RICH, FOR ME.
OUR SEASON IS COMING TO A CLOSE.
THE WEATHER IS ALREADY
STARTING TO GET COLD.
THE SNOW IS COMING DOWN
THE MOUNTAINS.
SO WE'RE IN A RACE
AGAINST TIME RIGHT NOW,
SO IT'S CRITICAL
THAT WE FIND SOME GOLD.
[ FRED LAUGHING ]
[ HOWLS ]
Carlos: UH-HUH?
Narrator: USING HIS
4,000-PSI GOLD BLASTER,
FRED CUTS INTO
COMPACTED MATERIAL
IN THE BASE
OF THE UPSTREAM WALL.
FIRST TIME EVER THAT I KNOW OF,
DUSTIN IS DOUBLE-DREDGING TODAY.
Narrator: WHILE FRED
BLASTS MATERIAL ABOVE HIM,
DUSTIN USES
BOTH DREDGE HOSES TOGETHER
TO TUNNEL TOWARDS
THE CRACK AT DOUBLE SPEED.
WE'VE GOT HURT ONE,
HURT TWO IN THE WATER.
THEY'RE ACTUALLY WORKING LIKE
A TEAM, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
TEAM HURT --
OUR FINAL PUSH TO GOLD.
NICE CHUNKY PIECE OF GOLD
IN THERE.
[BLEEP] MAN, WE GOT SOME GOOD
GOLD IN THERE, MAN.
IT'S IN THERE.
IT'S IN THE BOX.
IT'LL BE SAFE.
CRAZY, MAN.
Paul: ROCK! ROCK, ROCK, ROCK,
ROCK, ROCK, ROCK, ROCK.
LOOK OUT.
OH, YEAH. HEY!
WE GOT A LANDSLIDE.
DIVERS UP, DIVERS UP,
DIVERS UP.
DIVER COMING UP.
♪♪
Dustin: WE HAD A LANDSLIDE
THAT JUST ABOUT TOOK US OUT.
THAT'S THE WORST I'VE EVER
HAD RIGHT THERE, IS...
IT'S PRETTY DAMN BAD.
THE WAY WE WERE DIGGING IT,
WE JUST KEPT GETTING...
DIGGING ALONG THE BOTTOM.
IT JUST KEPT COMING IN.
I PUT BOTH NOZZLES TOGETHER,
AND IT...I THINK IT CAUSED...
THAT'S WHAT CAUSED THE CAVE-IN
BECAUSE I MADE THIS HUGE HOLE
WHERE I PROBABLY SHOULDN'T HAVE.
Narrator:
WHILE DREDGING UPSTREAM
TOWARDS THE NUGGET TRAP,
DUSTIN AND FRED
CREATED AN 18-FOOT WALL.
DUSTIN'S DOUBLE-DREDGING
UNDERMINED THE WALL,
LOOSENING LARGE
OVERHANGING ROCKS.
THEY FELL AND TRIGGERED
A LANDSLIDE.
♪♪
Dustin: HEY, FRED.
YOU CAN'T GO
DOWN THERE ANYMORE.
[BLEEP]
YOU'RE SHAKING.
YOU NEED TO GET IN...
YEAH, BUT I HAVEN'T HAD
WARM WATER IN A LITTLE WHILE.
WELL, YOU NEED TO GET
IN THE THING, IN THE ROOM.
I'M STILL HIGH OFF OF
MY ADRENALINE RUSH RIGHT NOW.
I KNOW.
THERE.
THIS IS THE WORST
IT'S EVER BEEN, RIGHT NOW.
IT'S SO BAD.
♪♪
Fred: WE DON'T KNOW HOW STABLE
THAT WALL IS.
THAT WHOLE THING
COULD COME COLLAPSING IN.
YOUR DAMN HEAD
IS LIKE A [BLEEP] PANCAKE.
DUSTIN COULD HAVE BEEN
ONE OF THEM, RIGHT THERE.
THAT'D BEEN...
...BASICALLY
THE END OF MY WORLD.
♪♪
Carlos:
BY THE END OF THE SEASON,
THE STRESS THAT FRED
IS FEELING RIGHT NOW...
CAN'T DREDGE.
CAN'T GET NO GOLD
FOR MY FAMILY, MAN.
WE'LL SEE WHAT HAPPENS, MAN.
STAY TUNED TILL THE END.
♪♪
ROUGH DAY TODAY.
I MESSED UP,
AND NOW I'VE GOT
GIGANTIC ROCKS EVERYWHERE.
Narrator: CHASING A FORTUNE
IN GOLD IN McKINLEY CREEK,
FRED AND DUSTIN CHEATED DEATH
WHEN A BOULDER
FELL INTO THEIR HOLE.
NOW, GOOD THING THAT THIS...
NOBODY GOT HURT, SO...
Narrator: THERE'S ONLY ONE WEEK
LEFT BEFORE THE HARSH
ALASKAN WINTER
ENDS THEIR SEASON,
BUT ALL DIVING IS ON HOLD UNTIL
THEY MAKE THE DIVE SITE SAFE.
Fred: WE'VE GOT TO CLEAN OFF
THOSE OVERHANGING ROCKS
OUT OF THAT WALL.
I MEAN, THEY ARE SERIOUS
ROCKS OUT THERE.
I WANT TO PULL THE ROCKS
OFF THE HILL AND PUT THEM
IN A SAFE PLACE
WAY DOWNSTREAM.
MAN,
WE DON'T HAVE TIME.
IF WE DRAG THOSE
BIG ROCKS DOWNHILL
AND OUT OF THE HOLE
AND BACK DOWNSTREAM,
IT'LL TAKE YOU
TWO WEEKS.
THAT'S MORE TIME TO GIVE
THE FLOODS A CHANCE TO COME
AND KILL US ALL
AND FILL IN OUR HOLE.
WE FAILED LAST SEASON,
AND I CAN'T LET
THAT HAPPEN AGAIN.
I KNOW WE CAN DO IT.
OH, THE HISTORY OF THIS PLACE,
THERE'S SO MUCH GOLD STILL HERE.
TOMORROW, WE'RE GONNA TRY
A DIFFERENT
AND FASTER SYSTEM.
WE'LL MAKE AN ATTEMPT
AT PULLING THEM BIG ROCKS,
AND WE'RE GONNA PULL
EVERYTHING UPSTREAM.
SINCE WE'VE ALL LEFT OUR
FAMILIES AND OUR BUSINESSES,
OUR JOBS BEHIND, IT'S A MUST
THAT WE FIND THE GOLD.
OTHERWISE, WE'RE ALL GOING
TO BE IN REALLY BAD SHAPE.
♪♪
Fred: AH, DUSTIN WANTS
TO PULL ROCKS UPSTREAM,
BACK UP THAT WAY A LITTLE WAYS,
GET IT OFF THE TOP OF US.
CARLOS, SO TODAY, WE ARE
GONNA BE RUNNING A LINE
GOING FROM BLUE
TO THAT BLOCK...
Carlos: YUP.
...BACK DOWN, AND WE'RE
GONNA DRILL ALL THESE
AND START DRAGGING THEM AND
STACKING THEM UP RIGHT THERE,
UNDERNEATH WHERE
THAT CHAIN IS.
PERFECT.
I LOVE IT.
Narrator: DUSTIN'S PLAN --
REROUTE THE WINCH
UPSTREAM THROUGH TWO PULLEYS,
ATTACH THE LINE TO EACH ROCK
WITH ANCHOR BOLTS
THEN DRAG THEM SAFELY UPSTREAM
OUT OF THE DIVE SITE.
Dustin: THIS IS DANGEROUS, LIKE,
EVEN JUST WHERE WE'RE STANDING
RIGHT NOW.
OH.
I LIKE THAT MUCH BETTER.
IF I CAN GET ENOUGH ROCKS
OUT OF THERE,
YOU COULD MAKE IT SAFE ENOUGH
FOR, WELL, US NOT TO DIE.
I'M STARTING TO LOOK AT IT.
WILL THAT FIT?
-IS IT GONNA HOLD?
-I THINK THIS WILL WORK.
-OKAY.
WE DEFINITELY CAN'T PULL THEM
DOWNSTREAM NOW
BECAUSE WE'VE GOT
TOO DEEP A HOLE.
Fred: WE COULD ALWAYS HAVE
THE POSSIBILITY
OF PULLING ANCHOR BOLTS OUT,
SOME OF THIS SHALE ROCK UP HERE
THAT'S NOT ALWAYS
IN THE BEST OF SHAPE.
WE'LL SEE IF IT WOULD HOLD,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
ALL YOU CAN DO
IS JUST GIVE IT A TRY.
Carlos: LIFT THE BIT.
THAT'LL WORK.
Narrator: TO ATTACH A CABLE
TO THE OVERHANGING BOULDERS,
A DIVER NEEDS TO POSITION
THE DRILL BIT.
ALL RIGHT.
PAUL, YOU GO DOWN.
LET'S START DRILLING BOULDERS
AND PULL THEM ALL BACK
AS FAR AS WE CAN
GET THEM OUT OF THE WAY.
Paul: YEAH.
BUT 75-YEAR-OLD FRED
HAS OTHER IDEAS.
Fred: DUSTIN, THAT WALL IS
JUST NOT SAFE ENOUGH
FOR ANYBODY
TO BE DOWN THERE,
SO I WILL GO DOWN AND ASSESS
THE SITUATION MYSELF
AND MAKE IT SAFE.
IS THERE ANY WAY I COULD
GET YOU ON WINCH
INSTEAD OF
IN THE WATER?
THE ROCKS -- YOU SAW
WHAT SIZE THEY WERE.
I'M JUST SCARED
YOU'RE GONNA DIE.
HE'S JUST NOT GOING
TO LISTEN TO ME.
HE JUST WON'T DO IT.
Wes: YOU KNOW, WE REALLY
WORRY ABOUT FRED
WHEN HE GOES DOWN LIKE THIS
BECAUSE HE IS THE OLDEST MAN
ON THE TEAM,
AND HE'S NOT THE FASTEST ANYMORE
AND NOT THE MOST AGILE.
Carlos:
WHAT CAN I SAY, MAN?
LET'S JUST PRAY FOR THE BEST,
WHICH I HAVE BEEN.
SO WE'RE JUST GONNA
DRILL THE HELL
OUT OF ALL THE TOP ROCKS
AND JUST KEEP GOING DOWN
FROM THE TOP.
OKAY, IF THAT'S
WHAT THE DEAL IS.
HEY, FRED.
LET'S JUST DO A FIRST
TEST RUN TO SEE
IF THE ANCHORS
ARE GONNA BLOW.
PAUL HAS GOT
A DRILL IN HAND,
AND HE'S READY
TO START DRILLING
[BLEEP] RIGHT THERE.
Narrator:
FRED ATTACHES ANCHOR BOLTS
TO THE LETHAL OVERHANGING ROCKS
SO THEY CAN BE DRAGGED UP
AND OUT OF THE DIVE SITE.
THE NEW UNTESTED PULLEY SYSTEM
COMES UNDER STRAIN
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
PAUL, YOU'RE IN
THE WORST SPOT EVER, DUDE.
IF THIS ANCHOR BLOWS,
IT'S GONNA CUT YOU IN HALF.
♪♪
UH...YEP...
YEAH.
YEAH!
[BLEEP]
THAT WAS FAST.
IT'S WORKING.
[ LAUGHS ]
Rich: EACH TIME WE GET ONE OF
THESE BIG PIGS OUT OF THERE,
THAT'S ONE STEP CLOSER
TO THE GOLD.
LET'S JUST START DRILLING
AND PUNCHING THEM.
DRILL AND PUNCH.
THIS IS GONNA BE REAL EASY,
I HOPE.
WE'RE GONNA BE
HITTING THIS SO HARD,
I WANT TO SEE THIS HOLE BACK
TO WHERE WE WERE IN NO TIME,
I MEAN, NO TIME.
WE HAVE TO GET
THIS DONE FAST.
-OH! OH, HO!
-MADE IT!
THAT WAS AWESOME!
A [BLEEP] NINJA, MAN.
THAT WAS
AN AWESOME CATCH.
ALL RIGHT.
CAN I GET RID OF THAT ROCK
COMING TOWARDS THE CAMP?
FRED,
YOU'RE IN A GOOD SPOT?
ALL RIGHT.
COMING UP, WES.
HERE WE GO.
COMING UP AND...SWING.
FRED. MOVE, MOVE,
MOVE, MOVE, MOVE.
FRED, FRED, FRED!
HE DOESN'T UNDERSTAND
WHY I DON'T WANT HIM
DOWN THERE.
Narrator: UP AHEAD...
LOOK AT THIS [BLEEP]
GOLD!
JUST [BLEEP]
WE KNEW WITHOUT A DOUBT
THAT THERE WAS GOLD
DOWN THERE.
♪♪
Wes: YEAH.
THAT [BLEEP] WASN'T IT?
Narrator: AT McKINLEY CREEK,
WINTER IS JUST
AROUND THE CORNER.
THE DAKOTA BOYS ARE WITHIN
STRIKING DISTANCE
OF A NUGGET TRAP THAT COULD
HOLD MILLIONS IN GOLD.
Dustin: IF IT DOESN'T FLOOD,
IT WILL SNOW,
AND EVERY SINGLE DAY
IS PRECIOUS.
IF WE DON'T GET A LOT OF WORK
DONE EVERY DAY,
WE WILL NEVER FINISH THIS.
I WILL SPEND THE REST OF MY LIFE
WONDERING WHAT THE HELL
IS DOWN THERE.
ANYBODY WHO DREDGES DOWN THERE
RIGHT NOW,
THE CHANCES OF DYING ARE HUGE.
Narrator: THEIR 18-FOOT HOLE IS
SURROUNDED BY LOOSE BOULDERS
THAT COULD FALL AT ANY TIME,
CRUSHING ANY DIVER BENEATH THEM.
TODAY IS ALL ABOUT TRYING TO
MAKE THIS SAFE FOR THE DIVERS.
THE GOAL IS TO TAKE THE FIRST
12 TO 15 FEET
OF GIANT HANGERS
OVER FROM MY HEAD.
Paul: TOMORROW
WE'LL GO IN A LITTLE...
THAT CRACK
AT THE BOTTOM.
Carlos:
THAT'S GOOD ENOUGH.
OKAY.
Fred: OOH, WHEE!
WE CAN'T PULL ON IT
UNTIL IT WIGGLES.
TODAY'S RULE --
IT MUST WIGGLE
BEFORE YOU PULL ON IT.
I'M GONNA HAND YOU DOWN
THE BLASTER.
I WOULD LIKE TO SEE IF YOU
CAN GET IT WIGGLED LOOSE,
BUT DON'T DROP IT
INTO THE [BLEEP] BOTTOM.
Narrator:
TO FREE THE WIDOW-MAKER,
FRED BREAKS UP THE MATERIAL
HOLDING IT IN PLACE
WITH HIS GOLD BLASTER.
♪♪
PAUL, SUIT UP!
AHH.
[BLEEP]
THAT'S LIKE CARRYING
A COUPLE BAGS OF CONCRETE.
WE HAVE GOT TO HAVE A LOT
OF WEIGHT ON OUR BACKS
BECAUSE THAT CURRENT IS SO BAD,
AND, LIKE, FOR ME, I'M SO LIGHT,
SO IT JUST WANTS
TO JUST TWIRL ME
LIKE I'M IN A WASHING MACHINE.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY FOR US
TO DO THIS.
BECAUSE, SEE, WE'VE GOT TO GET
OTHER DIVERS IN THERE.
WE CAN'T DO IT WITH JUST ONE
DIVER AND ONE DIVER ALONE,
AND WE GOT TO DO THAT
TO GET DOWN TO THE BOTTOM
TO GET TO THE GOLD.
NOBODY WANTS TO GET CRUSHED
BY ONE OF THOSE ROCKS.
YOU'D NEVER SEE THE ROCK COMING
AT YOU UNTIL AFTER IT HITS YOU.
Paul:
SO WHAT'S THE GAME PLAN?
I'M GONNA SEND YOU OVER HERE
WITH THE DREDGE,
AND IF YOU COULD EXPOSE
THAT BIG ROCK?
YUP.
LET'S RUN THEM,
GET THEM FREED UP.
THAT WOULD BE GREAT,
FROM THE BOTTOM.
Dustin: OKAY.
AHH.
♪♪
Narrator: THE PLAN --
TO DISLODGE THE WIDOW-MAKER
AND MAKE THE DIVE SITE SAFE,
McKINLEY VETERAN
PAUL RICHARDSON DREDGES
ON THE FACE OF THE WALL
WHILE FRED BLASTS MATERIAL
ABOVE HIM.
Dustin: YEAH.
AND, PAUL, YOU ARE TWISTED
[BLEEP] UP
ON THIS HOSE.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S RELAX.
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
JUST RELAX.
Paul: SHUT THIS OFF.
Narrator:
RICH TURNS OFF THE MOTOR
POWERING FRED'S GOLD BLASTER
TO CLEAR THE WATER.
PAUL NEEDS TO SEE.
FRED, YOU'RE NOT CUTTING
ANYMORE, ARE YOU?
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, PAUL.
YOU'RE COMING BACK, RIGHT?
AHH.
-ALL RIGHT, PAUL.
WE'RE...
YOU GOT TO COME UP, MAN.
PAUL IS
IN A SCARY SITUATION.
HE'S IN THE BOTTOM OF A HOLE,
AND HE CAN'T GET HIMSELF
UNTANGLED.
THE BOTTOM, RIGHT NOW,
IS A DANGER ZONE.
ALL RIGHT. CALM DOWN.
THIS IS A MESS.
I NEED YOU TO CALM DOWN,
FOR REAL.
LIKE, WHATEVER YOU'RE
DOING, STOP DOING IT.
I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TRYING TO DO.
I JUST NEED YOU TO QUIT IT
FOR JUST A SECOND.
CAN I PULL ON YOU
A LITTLE BIT?
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, PAUL.
I NEED YOU START BREATHING
LONG BREATHS, DUDE,
LONG BREATHS.
IF YOU HYPERVENTILATE,
YOU'RE GONNA PASS OUT.
PAUL.
PAUL...
I KNOW.
YOU NEED TO SLOW DOWN.
SLOW DOWN.
YOU CAN BREATHE.
IT'S OKAY.
CALM DOWN.
YOU'RE PANICKING, DUDE.
YOU'RE PANICKING.
SLOW DOWN.
STOP DOING WHAT
YOU'RE DOING, MAN.
YOU'RE FREAKING ME OUT.
PAUL, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
PAUL!
♪♪
ALL RIGHT.
Narrator: PAUL RICHARDSON'S
AIRLINE AND UMBILICAL
ARE TANGLED
AROUND HIS DREDGE HOSE,
TRAPPING HIM 18 FEET DOWN
IN THE DIVE HOLE
UNDERNEATH
A 1,500-POUND BOULDER.
PANIC KILLS, BRO.
FEAR KILLS, AND WHEN FEAR
AND PANIC GETS TOGETHER,
THAT'S LIKE A LOADED GUN
TO YOUR FRICKING HEAD, MAN.
DON'T GO DOWN THERE.
PAUL, I NEED YOU
TO CALM DOWN, DUDE.
YOU'RE FREAKING OUT.
YOU'RE GONNA HYPERVENTILATE,
AND THEN I CAN'T HELP YOU.
PAUL?
I NEED YOU
TO BREATHE, OKAY?
I NEED YOU TO SLOW
YOUR BREATHING DOWN.
I NEED YOU TO CALM DOWN.
THERE YOU GO.
THAT'S IT.
THAT'S IT, RIGHT THERE.
NEED TO HAVE YOU COME BACK,
ALMOST ALL THE WAY UP,
JUST OVER THE THRESHOLD
AND THEN BACK UNDER IT.
Paul: UGH.
CAN YOU MAKE IT UP?
ALL RIGHT.
HEY.
CONNECT THE HOSE TO THE WINCH,
AND LET'S PULL HIM UP.
WE HAVE AN IDEA
TO HELP YOU.
WE ARE THINKING ABOUT
PULLING THE HOSE
ALL THE WAY
BACK TO THE DREDGE.
GET HOOKED
INTO THE NOZZLE.
Narrator: CARLOS' PLAN --
ATTACH A CABLE
TO THE DREDGE NOZZLE
AND WINCH PAUL AND HIS HOSE
SAFELY UP OUT OF THE DIVE HOLE.
KEEP YOUR BREATHING
DOWN.
I JUST DON'T WANT YOU
TO PASS OUT.
PAUL!
JUST HOOK IT UP, SOMEBODY.
WE'RE COMING UP ON IT.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET HIM OUT OF HERE.
♪♪
OKAY.
YOU'RE OKAY.
YEAH, YEAH.
I GOT YOU.
[BLEEP]
THAT'S ALL GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
GOOD, YEAH.
-HOW ARE YOU, BROTHER?
-I'M GOOD.
YOU SCARED ME
FOR A SECOND, MAN.
SOMEHOW, I ACTUALLY TIED MYSELF
IN A KNOT
AROUND THE DREDGE HOSE.
YEAH, FOR A MOMENT, I PANICKED.
I DIDN'T WANT YOU
PASSING OUT.
YOU WERE CLOSE.
-YEAH.
WELL, I'M GLAD
YOU'RE STILL BREATHING, MAN.
IF IT HAPPENED AGAIN,
STOP EVERYTHING.
CALM THE [BLEEP] DOWN.
YEAH.
AND THEN EVERYTHING
BECOMES EASIER.
WANT TO TRY AGAIN?
UH, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
SLOW DOWN.
TAKE FIVE OR SIX BREATHS.
ALL RIGHT?
Narrator: CONQUERING HIS FEAR,
PAUL VOLUNTEERS TO GO BACK
AND REMOVE THE WIDOW-MAKER.
HOW YOU DOING
DOWN THERE?
COMING UP, BUDDY.
♪♪
Fred: [BLEEP]
THAT WAS OVER MY HEAD, HUH?
YUP.
GOOD JOB, MAN.
♪♪
Fred: WE PULLED ALL THE ROCKS
AND BIG HANGERS OFF THE WALL.
IT'S A WHOLE LOT SAFER FOR
THE DIVERS TO GO DOWN THERE NOW.
Narrator: AFTER A DAY'S WORK,
THE CREW CAN FINALLY GET BACK
TO DREDGING TOWARDS
THE NUGGET TRAP.
Dustin: EVERYTHING IS GOING
PERFECT RIGHT NOW.
-OH!
-TOUCHDOWN!
[ LAUGHTER ]
Paul: FELL?
-YEAH.
-UH-OH.
Fred: TELL ME THEY GOT
A GoPro ON THAT.
OH!
-[BLEEP]
DUSTIN FACE-PLANT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
Dustin:
I'M HAPPY TO DO IT, FRED.
COULDN'T HAVE HAPPENED
TO A BETTER GUY.
I GOT WATER ITCH.
YOU GOT FLEAS, FRED?
YEAH, WATER FLEAS.
TURNS MINE INTO DREADLOCKS.
Rich:
IF I HAD A BUNCH OF HAIR,
MINE WOULD DO THAT, TOO.
THAT'S WHY YOU DON'T.
YOU'VE BEEN IN IT TOO LONG.
Dustin: ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
WE HAD A GOOD DAY, BUT TOMORROW,
LET'S HIT IT HARD.
WE HAVE AN OPPORTUNITY
RIGHT NOW.
TWO WEEKS OF THAT CRACK,
I MEAN, WE'RE GETTING REALLY
FAR DOWN IN THERE.
IF THERE'S ANYTHING
DOWN HERE AT ALL,
I THINK THE GOLD
IS GONNA BE HUGE.
I GOT TO SEE WHAT'S GOING ON
DOWN THERE, DUDE.
LISTEN. MY FAMILY IS HUGELY
INVESTED IN THIS.
Paul: OUR BIGGEST THING
IS GONNA BE MOTHER NATURE.
WE GOT TO BEAT MOTHER NATURE.
Fred:
WELL, WE KNOW THAT.
YEAH.
WE KNOW THAT.
GOOD JOB TODAY.
-ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS.
GETTING THE GOLD MEANS
A BETTER LIFE
FOR MY BABY DAUGHTER, YOU KNOW?
THIS MEANS A BETTER LIFE
FOR MY FAMILY.
Dustin: I NEED TO FIND SOME GOLD
FOR THE CREW, FOR ME,
FOR EVERYONE.
[ SIGHS ]
IF THERE'S NOT GOLD THERE
IN THAT CRACK,
YOU'RE GONNA SEE
A GROWN MAN CRY.
SO I DON'T KNOW WHAT I WOULD DO.
♪♪
TODAY, MY GOAL IS TO GO DOWN
AND FINISH THIS HOLE.
I HOPE BY THE END OF THIS DAY,
I'LL HAVE FINISHED THE CRACK,
AND I'LL KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT'S DOWN THERE.
Narrator: FOR 3 1/2 MONTHS,
THE DAKOTA BOYS HAVE BATTLED
MOTHER NATURE, DIGGING 18 FEET
DOWN TO BEDROCK
AND PUSHING UPSTREAM
TO THE VERY DEEPEST SPOT.
THEY CAN NOW FINALLY FIND OUT
IF IT CONTAINS
A FORTUNE IN GOLD.
Fred: TOOK US WEEKS, MONTHS,
TO GET HERE.
WE'RE SO CLOSE TO SO MUCH GOLD.
I'M PERSONALLY HOPING
FOR NUGGETS.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, RICH AND I
ARE GOING DOWN TODAY.
IT'S BEEN A HARD SEASON.
YOU GUYS HAVE WORKED
YOUR ASS OFF,
BUT I NEED TO GET TO THE BOTTOM
AND SEE WHAT'S IN IT.
Paul: A THOUSAND OUNCES
WILL FIT IN A SMALL AREA.
IT ONLY TAKES
ONE POCKET.
-ONE SPOT.
-YEAH.
I DON'T HAVE THE MONEY
TO COME BACK HERE
AND DIG THIS HOLE AGAIN.
SO THIS IS THE ONLY CHANCE
WE HAVE TO FIND OUT
WHAT'S DOWN THERE.
Narrator:
AFTER TWO LONG HARD SEASONS,
DUSTIN AND RICH WILL NOW ATTEMPT
THEIR DEEPEST DIVE EVER,
HOPING TO REACH THOUSANDS
OF OUNCES OF GOLD.
MY FRICKING STOMACH AND CHEST
IS IN KNOTS RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS IT, MAN.
WE'RE AT THE END OF OUR JOURNEY,
GO HOME TO TELL MY FAMILY
THAT ALL OUR HARD WORK PAID OFF,
AND THIS HAS TO PAY OUT.
I WANT GOLD
IN MY POCKET.
I WANT TO FIND THE BOTTOM
AND FIND OUT
WHAT IT'S ABOUT.
Carlos:
FINISH IT, DUDE.
♪♪
GET IT, BROTHER.
GO GET IT.
YOU FIND
THAT GOLD FOR ME.
MY FAMILY
WILL THANK YOU, BRO.
THE WEATHER IS REALLY
CHANGEABLE HERE.
YOU COULD DEFINITELY
GET SNOWED IN OVERNIGHT.
WE HAVE TO WATCH OUR FORECAST
FOR ANY SIGNS OF RAIN
BECAUSE RAIN TURNS INTO SLEET
AND THEN SNOW.
I REMEMBER JOHN SCHNABEL.
HE USED TO CLOSE UP
USUALLY BY THIS TIME
BECAUSE HE SAID HE NEVER WANTED
TO GET CAUGHT BY SNOW,
AND IF SNOW HITS US,
THAT'S DEFINITELY THE END
OF YOUR SEASON.
♪♪
Fred:
DUSTIN, WHAT'S GOING ON?
Narrator:
WITH WINTER THREATENING
TO END THEIR SEASON,
DUSTIN AND RICH ARE DIVING
FOR THE LAST TIME,
CHASING A MONSTER PILE OF GOLD
IN A CRACK ON BEDROCK.
Carlos:
RICHARD IS CLEARING A PATH,
AND DUSTIN, HE'S COMING
RIGHT BEHIND HIM
AND PICKING IT UP.
Narrator: OVER TENS
OF THOUSANDS OF YEARS,
NUGGETS OF GOLD
WASHED DOWN THIS CREEK
AND SETTLED AT THE LOWEST POINT
ON THE BEDROCK.
WHEN THEY REACH THAT,
THEY'LL KNOW AT LAST
IF THEY'RE ALL GOING
TO BE RICH.
I WANT TO LOOK THERE.
THIS IS THE BASKET WE'RE PUTTING
ALL OUR EGGS INTO, RIGHT HERE.
Fred: DUSTIN?
YEAH, RIGHT NOW,
IT'S STARTING TO RAIN
A LITTLE BIT.
Rich: I DON'T THINK
WE'VE GOT THAT MUCH TIME.
IT'S A TIME BOMB
IF THIS THING FLOODS, MAN.
YEAH!
YEAH, YOU DID!
-[ LAUGHING ]
-WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
[BLEEP] YEAH.
[ LAUGHING ]
Narrator:
AFTER SEVEN HOURS,
THEY'VE DREDGED
THE ENTIRE LENGTH OF THE CRACK
AND SENT ANY GOLD UP
TO THE SLUICE BOX.
Fred: SOMETIMES, YOU'RE HOT.
SOMETIMES, YOU'RE NOT.
TODAY, WE WERE HOT.
YEAH!
-AHH!
-GOLD, BUDDY.
THAT'S IT, HUH?
-GOOD JOB!
-[BLEEP]
-WE GOT IT, FRED.
-GOOD JOB, MAN. GOOD JOB.
THANKS, BUDDY.
UGH.
A LOT OF EFFORT WENT INTO
DIGGING THIS HOLE OUT.
WHOO!
-OH, MY [BLEEP]
-[BLEEP] NUGGETS, BOYS!
-OH, [BLEEP] YEAH!
WHOO!
[ LAUGHTER ]
LOOK AT THOSE NUGGETS,
DUDE!
Fred: DUDE, DREDGING IN THAT
CRACK DID THE JOB.
I KNOW.
-[BLEEP]
-GOOD JOB, MAN.
OH, GOD, DUDE.
Dustin:
THIS IS EXCITING, THOUGH.
WE KNEW WITHOUT A DOUBT
THAT THERE WAS GOLD DOWN THERE.
I'M A LITTLE NERVOUS ABOUT
HOW MUCH IS IN THERE.
WE'LL DO A CLEANUP,
AND WE'LL FIND OUT WHAT WE GOT.
ALL RIGHT.
WHEW.
I WANT TO JUST FEEL THIS.
WE MADE THIS HAPPEN.
Fred: YOU LOOK BACK.
YOU SAY,
"LOOK WHERE WE ARE.
LOOK WHAT WE DID."
UNBELIEVABLE.
THIS IS THE END
OF A VERY LONG CHAPTER.
THINK ABOUT IT,
TWO SEASONS, MAN.
♪♪
WHEN YOU GET OLD,
AND YOU'RE GONNA GET OLD
ONE OF THESE DAYS,
YOU START REALIZING,
YOU LIVE ON MEMORIES.
WELL, I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE
FOR THIS DAY, MAN.
Wes: SO I'M CLEANING UP
OUR CONCENTRATES,
GETTING THE GOLD SEPARATED
FROM EVERYTHING ELSE.
I'M PRETTY IMPRESSED
WITH WHAT I'M SEEING.
WE DIDN'T KNOW IF
WE'D GET IN THE CRACK,
AND HERE WE ARE,
CLEANED IT OUT.
YOU SHOULD HOLD YOUR HEAD
UP HIGH FOR THAT.
LOOK AT THIS [BLEEP] GOLD!
Wes: THAT'S STARTING TO LOOK
PRETTY IMPRESSIVE, BOYS.
OH, MY [BLEEP]
THERE'S A LOT OF STUFF
IN THAT CARPET.
-I LOVE MY [BLEEP] JOB.
-YEAH, MAN.
THANK YOU, GUYS FOR [BLEEP]
STICKING WITH ME, MAN.
[BLEEP]
WE HAD CAVE-INS,
AND THE WALLS GOT DANGEROUS,
AND THINGS GOT REALLY
BAD AND SCARY, MAN.
BUT I'M GLAD Y'ALL SURVIVED
THIS [BLEEP]
[ LAUGHTER ]
LET'S GET IT WEIGHED UP
AND FIND OUT WHAT IT IS.
Narrator:
COMING UP ON THE SEASON FINALE
OF "GOLD RUSH: WHITE WATER"...
Dustin: WELL, WE GOT
SOME GOLD, GUYS,
MOMENT OF TRUTH.
[BLEEP]