SO, WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO REVEAL
OUR LITTLE SECRET WEAPON?
♪♪
OH, [BLEEP]
I KNOW WHAT IT IS!
OH, DUDE,
THIS IS AWESOME!
LET ME INTRODUCE YOU
TO THE GOLD BLASTER.
4,000 POUNDS OF PRESSURE.
BUT, I DON'T KNOW
IF IT'S TOTALLY SAFE.
♪♪
HEY, DUSTIN.
Yeah, I think
you're gonna like
that little toy.
WHAT?!
THIS IS CRAZY!
WHEN THERE'S TWO DIVERS
DOWN THERE,
I'M SCARED IT'S GONNA
CUT SOMEBODY'S ARM OFF.
♪♪
WE HAVE TO USE
A DANGEROUS WEAPON
AGAINST A DANGEROUS CREEK.
YOU GOT PRESSURE.
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
LET THE OLD MAN SHOW 'EM
HOW THE HELL IT'S DONE.
OLD MAN CAN ROCK.
PEOPLE HIS AGE
SHOULD BE IN NURSING HOMES,
EATIN' JELL-O AND, I DON'T KNOW,
WATCHING FRICKIN' "MURDER,
SHE WROTE"? I DON'T KNOW.
[ SUSPENSEFUL CHORD STRIKES ]
WE GOT A SITUATION
UP HERE.
[ FOUR GUNSHOTS ]
I'VE GOT TOO MUCH
INTO THIS, MAN.
I'M WILLIN' TO DIE FOR IT.
AIN'T NO AMOUNT OF GOLD
WORTH DYIN' FOR.
♪♪
Fred:
THE WHOLE HISTORY OF THIS VALLEY
IS GOLD HAS BEEN ON THE BEDROCK.
WE'RE ON THE RIGHT TRAIL.
WHOO! YEAH!
Paul:
THERE'S SMALL GOLD,
BUT IT'S CHUNKY.
[ CACKLES
DELIGHTEDLY ]
FINALLY FOUND BEDROCK,
[BLEEP]
--Captions by VITAC--
www.vitac.com
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
DISCOVERY COMMUNICATIONS
[ GUITAR PLUCKS
TRANQUIL TUNE ]
♪♪
PURE COMMERCIAL
WATER TODAY.
♪♪
WATER'S DOWN.
SUN IS SHINING.
GOT A LITTLE BIT OF VIS.
IT'S ON. IT'S TIME
TO GET SOME GOLD.
WE'RE GONNA GET TO THE
BOTTOM OF THIS DIG TODAY!
♪♪
HEY!
Narrator:
AFTER THREE MONTHS
DREDGING McKINLEY CREEK,
THE DAKOTA BOYS ARE
ABOUT TO HIT BEDROCK
AND A GOLD DEPOSIT
WORTH MILLIONS.
GONNA PUT THAT
DIP POLE IN THERE,
SEE WHAT WE GOT GOIN'.
HOPEFULLY, IT'S GOOD.
DUSTIN MUST RECOUP
HIS $75,000 INVESTMENT
BEFORE ANYONEGETS PAID.
-DUDE.
-HAVE FUN WITH THAT.
THAT'S A GOOD 12 FEET
RIGHT THERE, ANYWAY.
-OH, HELL, YEAH.
-YEAH!
MUSIC TO MY EARS RIGHT NOW.
[BLEEP]
IT'S A RACE TO THE GOLD.
Narrator:
LAST SEASON...
THEY HIT BEDROCK GOLD
AT 15 FEET.
LOOK AT THAT!
NOW, THEY HAVE JUST
THREE FEET TO GO.
WE'VE GOT A LIMITED
AMOUNT OF TIME.
RIGHT NOW,
WE'RE REALLYCLOSE.
IF EVERYTHING
GOES RIGHT TODAY,
I THINK WE'LL BE
ALL THE WAY ACROSS,
BEDROCK CLEANED.
-YEAH.
-WE BACKED DOWN THE HARDPACK.
WE HAVE NO MORE EXCUSES.
THIS IS IT.
IF WE BLOW IT,
IT'S OUR FAULT.
LET'S DO THIS.
Narrator:
75-YEAR-OLD FRED HURT,
THE CREW'S
MOST EXPERIENCED DIVER,
WILL BE LEADING THE MISSION.
YEAH, YEAH!
WELL, FRED'S KEEPIN'
THE TEAM ALIVE TODAY.
THE OLD GUY IS KICKIN' ASS.
WE'RE GONNA ATTACK THAT HARDPACK
THIS MORNING WITH THE CHIPPER.
WE CAN MAKE SOME HEADWAY
INTO THAT STUFF.
I'M GOIN' FOR THE BOTTOM.
I WANNA BE THE FIRST ONE
TO FIND THAT GOLD.
Narrator:
ALL THAT LIES BETWEEN THE CREW
AND THE GOLD ON BEDROCK
IS A LAYER OF COMPACTED
GRAVEL KNOWN AS HARDPACK.
THE AIR CHIPPER,
A PNEUMATIC CHISEL,
IS THE ONLY TOOL THEY HAVE
THAT CAN GET THEM
THROUGH TO THE GOLD.
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
ALL RIGHT, BUDDY, YOU
READY TO ROCK AND ROLL?
READY!
LET'S DO IT!
YEP, WE'RE GOOD.
HAVE A GOOD DIVE!
FIND THAT GOLD!
Gonna go get the gold!
Yeehoo!
GET SOME, BUDDY!
Whoo-hee!
[ UPBEAT BLUEGRASS PLAYS ]
Narrator:
JOINING FRED TODAY
IS FORMER MARINE SERGEANT AND
COMMERCIAL DIVER CARLOS MINOR.
I'M JUST GONNA TRY
TO DO MY JOB, BROTHER.
WHAT YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
DIG, DIG, DIG, MAN,
TO BEDROCK.
CARLO-O-O-O-S!
ON MY WAY!
[ LAUGHING ]
ON MY WAY.
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
GAME ON.
♪♪
Ooh!
Oh, hoo-hoo-hoo!
♪♪
[ SUSPENSEFUL CHORD STRIKES ]
THIS IS GOOD.
WE'RE BACK ON TRACK.
DECENT WEATHER, CLEAR WATER.
WE'RE READY
TO KICK SOME ASS.
♪♪
[ OUTRO PLAYS ]
GOT TO BE KIDDIN' ME!
♪♪
HE BREAKS [BLEEP] JUST
'CAUSE HE KEEPS ON RAMMIN'.
♪♪
Come up on the winch.
[ SUSPENSEFUL CHORD STRIKES ]
♪♪
Ooh...
Dustin:
FRED WON'T LISTEN
TO DIRECTIONS.
HE WON'T DO
WHAT WE WANT HIM TO.
HE JUST WANTS TO SHOW
THAT HE CAN STILL DO STUFF.
I'M STARTIN' TO GIVE UP
ON LIFE HERE.
FRED IS MAKIN' THIS
SO HARD FOR ME.
I DON'T SEE ANY WAY
FOR ME TO SUCCEED,
IF HE KEEPS MESSIN'
AROUND LIKE THIS.
♪♪
SO, HERE'S THE BOTTOM LINE:
FRED BROKE IT.
FRED WENT STRAIGHT DOWN.
DIDN'T CHIP HIS WAY,
A LITTLE BIT AT TIME,
HE JUST BURIED IT
TILL IT STUCK.
♪♪
YOU CAN'T SEE WHAT YOU'RE DOIN'
AND SOMETIMES YOU BURY IT
INTO THE HARDPACK
AND YOU TRY TO PULL IT OUT,
IT BREAKS THAT SPRING.
I'M NOT SURE WE
CAN CONTINUE WITH THAT.
Narrator:
WITHOUT THE AIR CHIPPER,
THE CREW WON'T GET
THROUGH THE HARDPACK TO GOLD
BEFORE WINTER ENDS THEIR SEASON.
♪♪
[ TRANQUIL TUNE PLAYS ]
SOME CRAZY IDEA I COME UP WITH
AND I THINK IT'LL WORK.
♪♪
WE'RE MAKIN' A LAST-DITCH
EFFORT TO GET THE GOLD
AND I THINK THIS WILL
HELP US DO IT.
♪♪
SO, WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO REVEAL
OUR LITTLE SECRET WEAPON?
[ OUTRO PLAYS ]
OH, [BLEEP]
I KNOW WHAT IT IS!
HERE, PULL THIS OUTTA HERE.
-OH, DUDE! THIS IS AWESOME!
-HERE. HERE, HERE.
JUST PICK IT UP.
THERE. ALL RIGHT.
JUST SET IT OFF ON THE
GROUND THERE A SECOND.
-OKAY.
-SECRET WEAPON IS
A PRESSURE WASHER.
40 YEARS AGO,
I USED TO CLEAN BARNACLES OFF
OF PYLONS WITH THOSE THINGS.
AND, IF YOU CAN CLEAN
BARNACLES OFF OF PYLONS,
YOU COULD BUST CONCRETE
WITH IT.
YOU COULD BUST --
YEAH.
WELL, WE GOT OUR HELICOPTER
COMIN' IN.
-WHOO!
JUST IN TIME!
Narrator:
FRED SPENT $5,000 ON THE
HEAVY-DUTY PRESSURE WASHER
TO REPLACE THE
AIR CHIPPER HE BROKE.
♪♪
Carlos:
YEE-HEE-HEE!
NOW, HE'S SPENDING
ANOTHER $2,000,
FLYING IT UP TO McKINLEY CREEK.
♪♪
CAN'T AFFORD HELICOPTERS
ANYMORE, MAN.
YOU WONDER WHY
I GET MAD WITH HIM.
♪♪
PUT YOUR ARMS OUT.
[ SUSPENSEFUL CHORD STRIKES ]
♪♪
DON'T GET PINNED
BETWEEN THAT ROCK.
[ ROTORS WHIRRING ]
WHAT?!
THIS IS CRAZY!
DUSTIN TO FRED.
HEY, DUSTIN.
Ah, it looks like
YOU GOT SOME --
SOME EXPENSIVE TOYS
DOWN HERE.
Hey, I think you're gonna
like that little toy.
THAT THING'S GONNA EAT
RIGHT THROUGH
THAT HARDPACK.
WELL, I HOPE IT WORKS, MAN.
A PRESSURE WASHER, HUH?
FRED AND HIS IDEAS.
HAVE YOU EVER USED A PRESSURE
WASHER UNDERWATER BEFORE?
NOT UNDERWATER.
WHAT I'M WORRIED ABOUT IS
IT'LL BE LIKE A JET SKI
UNDERWATER, LOSE CONTROL,
AND, WHEN THERE'S
TWO DIVERS DOWN THERE,
I'M SCARED IT'S GONNA
CUT SOMEBODY'S ARM OFF.
♪♪
[ SUSPENSEFUL CHORD STRIKES ]
[ GURGLING ]
[ MELANCHOLY TUNE PLAYS ]
[ GRUMBLE ]
♪♪
LET ME INTRODUCE YOU
TO THE GOLD BLASTER.
THERE'S THE NOZZLE,
PUTTIN' OUT
4,000 POUNDS OF PRESSURE.
THIS SHOULD TOTALLY
PULVERIZE THAT HARDPACK.
OH! COOL.
SLOW DOWN.
Narrator:
FRED HURT IS BANKING ON HIS NEW,
UNDERWATER PRESSURE WASHER,
THE GOLD BLASTER,
TO CUT THROUGH THE HARDPACK
AND, FINALLY, GET TO THE
GOLD-RICH BEDROCK.
WHERE ARE WE GOIN'
WITH IT?
[ TRANQUIL MUSIC PLAYS ]
THE GOLD BLASTER
PACKS WAY MORE POWER
THAN A HOUSEHOLD
PRESSURE WASHER,
SO FRED'S ADDED
A SAFETY MECHANISM.
WHEN YOU SHUT IT OFF,
BY LETTIN' GO OF THE TRIGGER,
IT FALLS OUT OF THE BOTTOM
AND SHUTS IT OFF.
BUT, I DON'T KNOW
IF IT'S TOTALLY SAFE.
I HAVE NOT TRIED IT OUT
UNDERWATER.
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
Narrator:
THE MOTOR COMPRESSES WATER
TO 4,000 PSI
AND FEEDS IT
TO FRED'S GOLD BLASTER.
THE PRESSURIZED JET
SHOULD EASILY
BREAK THROUGH THE HARDPACK.
♪♪
I LOST SLEEP OVER THIS
LAST NIGHT
AND I KNOW HOW DANGEROUS THIS IS
AND I WARNED ALL THE GUYS,
"HEY, YOU MIGHT DIE
DOWN THERE TODAY."
AND HE'S LIKE, "HEY,
I GOT THIS GIMMICKY THING.
MAYBE I COULD DO
SOMETHING BIG DOWN THERE,"
AND I'M THINKIN',
"YOU SHOULD STAY OUT,
'CAUSE YOU'RE GONNA DIE.
IT'S REALLY DANGEROUS
DOWN THERE."
♪♪
I MEAN, THAT'S 4,000 POUNDS
OF PRESSURE
COMING OUT OF THE END
OF THAT NOZZLE,
SO, IF IT GETS AWAY FROM YA,
IT'LL BE LIKE THE OLD TOYS
WE USED TO HAVE WHERE IT
JUST FLOPS AROUND EVERYWHERE
WITH THE WATER BLOWIN' OUT,
EXCEPT THIS'LL BE DEADLY.
[ TRANQUIL TUNE PLAYS ]
HOW'S THAT FEEL?
FEELS GOOD.
♪♪
ARE YOU READY?
I'M GONNA FIRE IT UP!
♪♪
CAN YOU GO AHEAD
AND CLEAN THE DECK?
OH, NICE!
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
♪♪
[ MOTOR STARTS ]
YOU GOT PRESSURE!
Wow!
♪♪
Whee-hoo!
[ Laughs ]
Yeah!
♪♪
[ Laughing ]
[ TRANQUIL TUNE PLAYS ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
♪♪
WELL, MY NEW TOY IS
JUST BUSTIN' ASS
DOWN THERE.
THAT HARDPACK, IT JUST EATS
THAT STUFF ALIVE.
IT JUST PULVERIZES IT.
MAYBE THEY JUST NEED
TO GROW A BIT --
A BIT BIGGER COJONES.
♪♪
[ LAUGHING ]
LET THE OLD MAN SHOW 'EM
HOW THE HELL IT'S DONE.
[ CHORD STRIKES ]
♪♪
SO, WHADDA WE GOT?
THERE YOU GO, RIGHT THERE.
THERE'S THE EDGE
OF THE HOLE.
IT'S 14.5 FEET
RIGHT THERE, FRED.
IT'S GONNA WORK.
THAT'S GONNA GET US
THERE FAST, FRED.
WE'RE GETTIN' CLOSE.
Narrator:
FRED'S GOLD BLASTER HAS GOT THEM
TO JUST SIX INCHES FROM BEDROCK.
WE HAVE TO USE A POTENTIAL
DANGEROUS WEAPON
AGAINST A DANGEROUS CREEK.
FIGHT FIRE WITH FIRE.
GOOD DEAL, FRED.
GOOD FRICKIN' DEAL.
♪♪
[ CHORD STRIKES ]
Dustin:
I SERIOUSLY BELIEVE WE'RE ONLY,
LIKE, SIX OR EIGHT INCHES,
BUT THAT'S HOW MY BRAIN WORKS.
IT'S 10 INCHES AWAY,
ONE FOOT AWAY.
ONLY ONE MORE FOOT.
IT'S HOW MY BRAIN WORKS.
I'M JUST WIRED
THAT WAY.
Narrator:
THE DAKOTA BOYS ARE DETERMINED
TO HIT A PILE OF GOLD
ON THE BEDROCK
BENEATH THE CREEK.
♪♪
DIVING WITH DUSTIN TODAY.
HE'S A GOOD
DIVE PARTNER.
WE SEEM TO KICK ASS
DOWN THERE.
♪♪
-ALL RIGHT.
-READY!
♪♪
Narrator:
THE ONLY WAY TO GET
THROUGH THE HARDPACK
IS WITH FRED'S
4,000-PSI GOLD BLASTER.
[ CHORD STRIKES ]
IT SEEMS SOMETIMES THAT,
EVERY IDEA I COME UP WITH,
DUSTIN, HE DOESN'T LIKE IT.
UH, THERE'S SOME KIND
OF RESISTANCE.
I HAVE NEVER SAID, "OH, WELL,
WHY DON'T WE DO IT THIS WAY?"
AND DUSTIN SAID, "YEAH,
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
LET'S JUST DO THAT."
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
♪♪
HOW'S THAT GOLD BLASTER
WORKIN', DUSTIN?
Uh...
HE'S MELTIN' IT, MAN.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
HE'S DOING, IS MELTIN' IT.
HOT WATER IN SNOW, BRO.
HOT WATER IN SNOW.
♪♪
IT REALLY FEELS GOOD THAT
DUSTIN ACTUALLY APPRECIATED
AND LIKED SOMETHING
THAT I SUGGESTED AND,
UH, IT'S A GOOD FEELING.
[ LAUGHING ]
WE KEEP THIS UP,
WE'LL HIT THAT BOTTOM.
ALL RIGHT, BASKET UP.
♪♪
HEY, DUS!
HOW'S THE PRESSURE
WASHER WORK?
GOLD BLASTER WORKS AWESOME.
Narrator:
FRED'S GOLD BLASTER IS
SLICING THROUGH THE HARDPACK,
BUT THERE'S STILL
NO SIGN OF BEDROCK.
SO, I'VE GOT ABOUT
15 FEET RIGHT THERE
AND IT STILL FEELS
GRAVELLY ON THE BOTTOM.
DOESN'T FEEL LIKE BEDROCK YET.
HOW DEEP CAN WE
ACTUALLY GO WITH THIS?
WE DON'T START GETTING SOME
SUBSTANTIAL GOLD PRETTY SOON,
IT'S GONNA BE HARD
TO KEEP WANTIN' TO GO HERE.
I'M 15 FEET DEEP.
I'VE SEEN GOLD 15 FEET
DOWN IN THAT HOLE.
WE THOUGHT THAT WOULD BE
ABSOLUTELYTHE DEEPEST
IT WOULD EVER BE.
WE'RE AT 15 FEET AND IT DOESN'T
LOOK LIKE WE HIT THE BOTTOM YET.
I COULD BE SIX INCHES
AWAY, OR SIX FEET.
WHAT THE [BLEEP]
ARE WE DOIN' HERE?
♪♪
WHERE IN THE WORLD
DOES THIS THING END?
♪♪
I DON'T KNOW.
I REALLY DO NOT KNOW.
Narrator:
THEY'RE 15 FEET DOWN
AND EVERYTHING THEY LEARNED
LAST SEASON IS NOW IN DOUBT.
WE COULD BE TWO FEET AWAY,
ONE FOOT AWAY,
SIX INCHES AWAY, YOU KNOW?
♪♪
HUMAN SPIRIT, BROTHER.
HUMAN SPIRIT, MAN.
WHAT ARE YOUMADE OUT OF,
YOU KNOW?
[chuckling] WHAT
ARE YOU MADE OUT OF?
[ SUSPENSEFUL CHORD STRIKES ]
♪♪
[ GURGLING ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
♪♪
ANOTHER DAY
IN THE DREDGE HOLE.
[ SUSPENSEFUL CHORD STRIKES ]
♪♪
Wes:
IT'S BEEN A ROUGH WEEK.
WE'VE GOT TO HIT
THIS GOLD SOON,
'CAUSE EVERYBODY
IS JUST COMPLETELY WORN OUT.
I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH LONGER
OUR BODIES CAN ACTUALLY
LAST TO DO THIS.
♪♪
OHH.
Narrator:
THE DAKOTA BOYS' SPEND
IS NOW OVER $80,000.
IF THEY DON'T GET GOLD BEFORE
WINTER ENDS THEIR SEASON,
THERE'LL BE NO PAYDAY.
I'VE GOT TOO MUCH
INTO THIS, MAN.
I'M WILLIN'
TO DIE FOR IT.
[ LAUGHING ]
AIN'T NO AMOUNT OF GOLD
WORTH DYIN' FOR.
IF IT'S GONNA GET TO THAT POINT,
THEN IT'S GONNA BE TIME TO MOVE.
I WISH I COULD SAY THAT
TO MY BRAIN.
YOU CAN.
Narrator:
THE CREW IS BEING PUSHED
TO THE LIMIT
AND QUESTIONING HOW DEEP THEY
NEED TO GO TO HIT BEDROCK GOLD.
♪♪
Dustin:
IT'S PAST 15 FEET,
SO WE MUST'VE MADE
A MISTAKE LAST TIME.
BEDROCK'S GOTTABE
DOWN THERE.
WE JUST GOTTA KEEP DIGGIN'.
♪♪
WE'RE READY TO GET IN.
EVERYBODY WARMED UP?!
LET'S GET THIS DONE!
DO IT NOW, OR FOREVER
WONDER WHAT'S DOWN THERE.
HOW 'BOUT THAT?
♪♪
TODAY, I TRY TO GET
TO THE BOTTOM.
WE ALL BEEN KILLIN'
OURSELVES.
SOMEBODY NEEDS TO TAKE US
ACROSS TO THAT FINISH LINE.
♪♪
I'M REALLY HOPIN' THERE'S
A NICE, FAT, GOLD LAYER
SITTIN' ON TOP OF BEDROCK.
HAVE A GOOD DIVE, MAN.
JUST LET ME KNOW
WHAT YOU NEED.
COPY THAT.
♪♪
LOOK AT THAT!
YOU SEE THAT?
YOU SEE THAT ROCK?
THAT ROCK?
WOW!
THAT ROCK COULD FALL DOWN
AND KILL SOMEBODY.
LOOK! THAT THING.
YOU GET THOSE ROCKS
FROM WAY ABOVE
IN THE HOLES
RIGHT DOWN THERE.
BOW!
♪♪
Narrator:
OVER 18 FEET DOWN
AND DEEP INTO THE HARDPACK,
THE WALLS OF THE DIVE HOLE
ARE NEAR-VERTICAL.
THE FORCE OF THE GOLD BLASTER
IS LOOSENING
OVERHANGING BOULDERS
THAT COULD EASILY FALL
AND CRUSH THE DIVERS.
[ SUSPENSEFUL CHORD STRIKES ]
WE'RE NOT TALKIN' ABOUT PEBBLES,
THE LITTLE THINGS LIKE THIS.
WE'RE TALKIN' ABOUT A ROCK
THAT IS THIS BIG AND LIKE THAT.
IF YOU'RE LAYIN'
DOWN IN THE BOTTOM,
YOU'RE WORKIN' AND ONE
OF THE THINGS LANDS ON YOU,
THAT COULD BURY YOU
RIGHT THERE.
♪♪
[ SUSPENSEFUL CHORD STRIKES ]
[ SINISTER CHORD STRIKES ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
GET HIM OUTTA THERE!
QUICK! BRING HIM UP,
BRING HIM UP.
QUICK, BRING HIM UP,
BRING HIM UP!
[ SINISTER CHORD STRIKES ]
Man: IS DUSTIN OKAY?
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
PAUL, IS HE OKAY?!
[ SINISTER CHORD STRIKES ]
[ MELANCHOLY TUNE PLAYS ]
WHEW! WHOO-HOO!
♪♪
I WAS CUTTIN' THE SHAFT
RIGHT HERE,
ALL THE WAY INTO THIS WALL,
WHEN, ALL OF A SUDDEN,
THE WATER,
IT WAS AN OBVIOUS LANDSLIDE.
IT SOUNDED LIKE A RUMBLIN'
TRAIN COMIN' THROUGH.
UNDERWATER,
YOU DON'T JUST HEAR IT.
YOU FEEL IT.
IT JUST SMASHES
YOUR CHEST IN.
PKKH-RRRRRUH!
BIG BOULDER FELL FROM SOMEWHERE
AND IT JUST WENT PITCH-BLACK.
THE [BLEEP] SIDES ARE SO STEEP
AND WE'RE SO DEEP,
THAT'S, LIKE, A HUGE RECIPE
FOR DISASTER, MAN.
I'M TELLING YOU.
HOWEVER YOU WANNA
COOK IT, MAN,
IT'S GONNA TASTE REALLY BAD.
♪♪
[ GURGLING ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
♪♪
Narrator:
WINTER IS CLOSING IN.
THE DAKOTA BOYS HAVE DREDGED
FOR FIVE DAYS,
DOWN TO 18 FEET,
AND HAVE STILL
NOT HIT BEDROCK.
ALL RIGHT, UH, WE'RE GONNA
DO A CLEANUP, GUYS,
FIND OUT IF THERE'S ANY GOLD.
Paul:
IT WOULD BE A BIG
MORALE BOOSTER
FOR EVERYBODY TO SEE
GOLD IN THE BOX.
THE LATER IN THE SEASON WE GET
AND LESS GOLD WE SEE,
THE MORE DOWN EVERYBODY GETS.
IT'S A GOOD ADVENTURE,
BUT, WITHOUT THE GOLD...
THAT'S WHAT EVERYBODY'S
FAMILY'S COUNTIN' ON.
WE REALLYNEED A LOTTA
GOLD IN THE BOX.
[ SINISTER MUSIC PLAYS ]
YEAH, ACTUALLY,
THIS BOX IS LOOKIN'
A LITTLE DEPRESSING, MAN.
SINCE WE HAD THAT LAST FLOOD,
OUR GOLD HAS JUST QUIT.
WE'RE NOT GETTIN' ANYTHING.
-NO.
-I MEAN,
-YEAH.
-NOTHIN'.
-YEAH, WE'RE NOT GETTIN' [BLEEP]
-NOPE.
-Carlos: IT SUCKS, MAN.
-YEAH.
-WE GOT NO GOLD, BRO.
MAN, THAT MAT SHOULD HAVE
ALL KINDS OF GOLD IN IT.
IT DOESN'T HAVE ANYTHING.
RIGHT HERE? THIS LOOK
YOU SEE ON MY FACE, MAN,
THIS IS A SPIRIT
TRYIN' TO KEEP STRONG, BRO.
♪♪
THERE'S NO GOLD
IN THE BOX RIGHT NOW
THAT YOU
CAN VISIBLY SEE.
WE'VE SPENT A LOTTA TIME
ON THIS HOLE RIGHT HERE,
GETTIN' DOWN DEEP,
AND NOTHING.
NOTHIN'S COMIN' OUT
OF THE HARDPACK, NOTHIN'.
YEAH.
HERE'S THE PROBLEM.
WE MADE A DECISION.
YEAH.
YOU EITHER STICK WITH IT NOW
OR ABANDON ALL HOPE.
THE LAST COUPLE OF WEEKS,
WE HAVEN'T GOTTEN ANYTHING.
I-I UNDERSTAND THAT.
EVERYTHING RIGHT NOW IS
TELLING ME TO GO UPSTREAM.
I AGREE.
I THERE'S GOLD DOWN THERE,
IT'S ALL IN BEDROCK
AND, IF I'M A COUPLE FEET AWAY
FROM BEDROCK RIGHT NOW,
I'D SURE LIKE
TO [BLEEP] FIND OUT.
THE FARTHER
WE GO UPSTREAM,
IT COULD GET BETTER
AND BETTER.
YOU THINK.
NO, I KNOW.
YOU THINK YOU KNOW.
YOU DON'T KNOW.
IF YOU DON'T FINISH OUT
THE [BLEEP] HOLE,
YOU DIG A HOLE HERE,
A HALF-HOLE THERE,
A HALF-HOLE THERE.
YEP.
COMMIT TO THIS
OR YOU DIG
LITTLE HOLES EVERYWHERE.
FINISH IT.
FIND OUT.
♪♪
YOU KNOW, THE CREW
IS STARTIN' TO FALL APART
QUITE A BIT ACTUALLY,
RIGHT NOW,
AND EVERYBODY'S GOT AN OPINION
WHERE THE GOLD'S AT,
SO I HAVE TO STAND STRONG.
WE EITHER ALL WORK ON ONE
THING AND GET IT FINISHED
OR SPEND THE REST
OF OUR LIVES
WONDERIN' WHAT THE HELL
IS DOWN THERE.
I NEED TO GET TO BEDROCK.
OTHERWISE, WE JUST WASTED
ANOTHER SEASON.
Narrator: FORTUNATELY,
DUSTIN HAS ONE ALLY:
HIS DAD.
THE WHOLE HISTORY
OF THIS VALLEY IS ALWAYS
GOLD HAS BEEN ON THE BEDROCK.
THAT FORMATION HAS BEEN DOWN
THERE FOR THOUSANDS OF YEARS.
NO ONE HAS EVER
DISTURBED THAT.
WE'RE ON THE RIGHT TRAIL.
WE NEED TO FIND OUT WHAT IS
UNDER THAT HARDPACK.
AND THEY WANNA QUIT?
[laughs] FAT CHANCE.
[ CLUCK ]
♪♪
[ SIGH ]
ANOTHER DAY.
♪♪
[ TRANQUIL TUNE PLAYS ]
AH! YOU OKAY?
OH!
YOU LOOKIN' FOR MAMA.
YOU BETTER NOT LEAVE THAT TREE
TILL YOU KNOW WHERE MAMA IS.
I BETTER KNOW
WHERE MAMA IS.
♪♪
GIVE HIM A HAND
WITH THAT BARREL.
[singsong]
NAILED IT!
HEY, MAN, WE GOT
A SITUATION UP HERE.
-WHAT'S GOING ON?
-WE GOT A BABY BEAR
THAT WON'T RUN AWAY.
-AWW.
-AND WE DON'T KNOW
WHERE MAMA BEAR IS.
-ALL RIGHT.
OHHH, THAT'S AWESOME!
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
ALL RIGHT, WATCH YOUR EARS,
EVERYBODY.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA
DO WITH IT?!
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA,
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?!
♪♪
JUST SCARE HIM.
[ LAUGHING ]
[laughing]
"WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?"[ LAUGHING ]
[ FOUR GUNSHOTS ]
♪♪
[ GUNSHOT ]
BEAR'S OUTTA HERE,
GUYS.
LITTLE BABY BEAR'S GONE.
HOPEFULLY, MAMA'S NOT
BEHIND HIM, SO.
JUST WARNING SHOTS.
♪♪
[ SUSPENSEFUL CHORD STRIKES ]
Narrator:
THE DAKOTA BOYS ARE MINING
THE DEEPEST,
MOST TREACHEROUS DIVE HOLE
THEY'VE EVER DREDGED.
VETERAN DIVER FRED HURT
IS UP FOR THE CHALLENGE.
♪♪
I AM NOT GONNA GIVE UP.
I'M JUST TOO CLOSE
TO THE BOTTOM, I THINK.
I WOULD HATE TO SAY THAT I QUIT
THREE FEET FROM THE BOTTOM.
[laughs]
OR FIVE FEET FROM THE BOTTOM.
NOW, FRED'S THE ONLY ONE
THAT AGREES WITH ME,
THAT WE SHOULD DIG STRAIGHT
DOWN TO THE BEDROCK.
EVEN THOUGH IT'S
DANGEROUS DOWN THERE,
FRED, RIGHT NOW,
IS THE ONLY ONE
THAT'S CRAZY ENOUGH
TO GO DOWN THERE.
♪♪
BEAUTIFUL DAY!
WHAT COULD POSSIBLY
GO WRONG?
YEAH, RIGHT.
Narrator:
CARLOS IS COMMITTED
TO REACHING BEDROCK,
BUT HIS SOON-TO-BE BRIDE
IS ON HER WAY
UP TO HAINES, ALASKA,
FOR THEIR CHURCH WEDDING.
BEFORE SHE WALKS
DOWN THE AISLE,
CARLOS IS TAKING
ONE MORE DIVE ALONGSIDE FRED.
THIS IS NOT A MANLY THING.
IF I WAS IN YOUR SITUATION,
I PROBABLY WOULD BACK OFF.
IMMA TELL YOU THE TRUTH.
I DON'T HAVE A FAMILY
OR CHILDREN OR ANY OF THAT
STUFF TO TAKE CARE OF,
SO I FEEL COMFORTABLE GOIN'
DOWN THERE AND RISKIN' MY LIFE.
THIS IS REAL DANGER.
-YEAH, I'VE BEEN IN SITUATIONS
LIKE THIS LOTS
OF TIMES, MAN.
WELL, THERE YOU GO.
THAT'S ON YOU.
-YEAH, YEAH.
-I JUST NEED YOU TO KNOW THAT.
NO, OF COURSE.
DON'T GET YOURSELF KILLED
OVER THIS.
IT'S UP TO YOU NOW.
COMPLETELYUP TO YOU.
I KNEW ABOUT ONE OR TWO
DIVERS IN MY WORK TIME
WHERE THEY GOT BURIED ALIVE.
YOU GET BURIED DOWN THERE,
THAT'S GONNA SEEM LIKE
FOR A MILLION YEARS,
TILL SOMEBODY COMES
AND DIGS YOU OUT.
♪♪
ALL THE WAY DOWN,
WHEN I WAS DROPPIN' IN,
THERE'S HANGERS STICKIN'
OUT OF THE WALLS.
I CAN'T TELL YA
ENOUGH, MAN.
JUST REALLY WATCH
YOUR ASS, FRED.
♪♪
Rich:
IT IS A NAIL-BITING
EXPERIENCE,
EVERY MINUTE THAT YOU'RE DOWN
IN THE BOTTOM OF THAT HOLE.
I WAS SCARED [BLEEP]
YESTERDAY FOR SOME TIME.
♪♪
Dustin:
IT'S NOW OR NEVER.
IF YOU RELAX RIGHT NOW,
YOU'RE GONNA SPEND
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE
WONDERIN' WHAT'S DOWN THERE,
'CAUSE YOU'RE NOT GONNA
GET TO IT.
I HAVE TO HIT BEDROCK
OR MY CREW'S GONNA QUIT ON ME.
♪♪
[ EERIE MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL CHORD STRIKES ]
Aaaaaaah!
[ SINISTER CHORD STRIKES ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ EERIE MUSIC PLAYS ]
Narrator:
FEAR OF BEING BURIED ALIVE
HAS FORCED CARLOS
TO ABANDON HIS DIVE.
DUDE, I'M SCARED.
-I KNOW YOU ARE.
-I-I-I--
-YEAH.
-BUT THE THING IS,
IT WAS JUST TOO --
-I GET IT.
Carlos:
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME SINCE
THE SEASON THAT I GOT SCARED.
I'M [BLEEP] TERRIFIED.
I'M TERRIFIED.
I DON'T CARE --
CRIED OR NOT, MAN.
I'M [BLEEP] TERRIFIED.
THAT THING COMES
DOWN ON ME,
YOU'RE NOT GETTING ME
OUT OF THERE.
I LOVELOOKIN' FOR GOLD,
BUT I WANNA BE AROUND
TO SPEND MY GOLD,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
♪♪
[ GURGLING ]
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ GUNFIRE ]
CEASE FIRE, GUYS.
CEASE FIRE.
GOT SOME GOOD NEWS
TO TELL YOU GUYS.
THIS SATURDAY,
YOU GUYS ARE INVITED
TO MY WEDDING.
-Both: HELL, YEAH.
-WHAT?!
-CONGRATULATIONS.
IT WOULDN'T BE THE SAME
WITHOUT YOU GUYS,
SO I'M DOIN' IT HERE,
IN ALASKA, MAN.
TONIGHT'S MY BACHELOR PARTY.
LET'S JUST SHOOT IT UP.
-WHOO!
-SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN!
HIT IT.
[ GUNFIRE ]
DAMN!
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ GUNSHOT ]
♪♪
GLAD YOU GUYS ARE HERE, MAN,
SERIOUSLY, MAN.
I'M GLAD YOU GUYS
MADE IT, MAN.
Officiant:
ALL RISE, PLEASE.
WE WELCOME ALL OF YOU HERE TODAY
TO JOIN CARLOS AND TERESA
IN THE HOLY BOND
OF MARRIAGE.
CARLOS, YOU MAY KISS
YOUR BRIDE.
[ LAUGHS ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ GUEST LAUGHING ]
[ TENDER TUNE PLAYS ]
THAT WAS REALLY GOOD.
I LIKED THAT.
HE'S DESERVED IT.
I'M HAPPY FOR HIM.
THIS IS GREAT.
HE'S MY BOY.
-OH, IT'S A GREAT DAY!
IT'S A AWESOME DAY.
-YOU GOT HIM FOR TOMORROW.
WE GOT HIM BACK MONDAY.
-[LAUGHING]
YEAH! GOOD DEAL.
♪♪
[ GURGLING ]
[ SINISTER MUSIC PLAYS ]
♪♪
Narrator:
AFTER THE CELEBRATIONS
OF CARLOS'S ALASKAN WEDDING,
IT'S BACK TO RISKING
LIFE AND LIMB
18 FEET BENEATH McKINLEY CREEK,
ATTEMPTING TO GET GOLD
ON BEDROCK.
♪♪
All right, Fred,
you're on your own.
Now, get to the
bottom, man.
VETERAN MINER FRED IS
IN THE DANGER ZONE,
WHILE DUSTIN SUPERVISES
FROM ABOVE.
TRYIN' TO PUSH FRED TO REALLY
GET DOWN TO THE BOTTOM,
BECAUSE I THINK
THIS IS OUR LAST CHANCE.
Good luck down there, man.
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
I HOLD ON TO HOPE, THINKIN',
IN A COUPLE DAYS,
I CAN GET FILTHY GOLD RICH.
THERE COULD BE NOTHIN'
DOWN THERE.
WOULDN'T BE A WASTE OF TIME.
MAKE A EDUCATED GUESS OF WHERE
YOU THINK THE GOLD'S AT.
YOU STICK TO IT AND YOU WORK
YOUR ASSOFF TO GET DOWN TO IT.
YOU PUSH AND PUSH AND PUSH,
PAST YOUR BREAKIN' POINT.
ONE MORE FOOT.
ONE MORE FOOT. ONE MORE FOOT.
JUST KEEP DIGGIN'.
JUST ONE MORE FOOT.
THIS COULD CHANGE
MY ENTIRE LIFE.
♪♪
[ SUSPENSEFUL CHORD STRIKES ]
[ TRIUMPHANT MUSIC PLAYS ]
WHOO! YEAH! HOO! COME ON.
FINALLY, WE HIT
WHAT WE'RE LOOKIN' FOR.
Rich:
THIS IS EPIC [BLEEP]
IT'S THIS HUGE ACCOMPLISHMENT
OF SIMPLY REACHING THE BOTTOM
OF McKINLEY CREEK.
IF THERE WAS BIG, HONKIN'
FARMER NUGGETS RIGHT NOW,
THEY WOULDN'T BE ABLE
TO SEE 'EM.
[ CACKLES
DELIGHTEDLY ]
FINALLY FOUND BEDROCK,
[BLEEP]
GOOD JOB, FRED!
♪♪
FRED DID AWESOME TODAY.
HE'S FEARLESS.
HE JUST TUNNELS DOWN WHEN
NOBODY ELSE IS GOIN' TO.
HE'S TAKING CHANCES.
THAT'S FOR DAMN SURE.
[ LAUGHING ]
LOVE IT!
75 YEARS OLD.
OLD MAN CAN ROCK.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I MEAN, PEOPLE HIS AGE
SHOULD BE IN NURSING HOMES,
EATIN' JELL-O
AND, I DON'T KNOW,
WATCHING FRICKIN' "MURDER,
SHE WROTE"? I DON'T KNOW.
Paul:
I CAN TELL YOU NOW: NOBODY'S
GONNA WANNA GIVE UP NOW.
I THINK GETTIN' TO BEDROCK WAS
A BIG BOOST FOR EVERYBODY.
THAT WAS SOMETHING
WE REALLYNEEDED TO DO
BEFORE IT GOT WAY TOO DEEP.
-SO YOU CAN SEE IT?
-[CHUCKLE]
HEY, THERE'S SMALL GOLD,
BUT IT'S CHUNKY.
CHECK THIS OUT.
THAT IS A REALLY GOOD SIGN.
IT MAY NOT BE TODAY
THAT WE GET THE BEST GOLD,
BUT WE'RE ON BEDROCK NOW.
IT'S JUST NOT EVEN
THE SAME GAME.
[ OUTRO PLAYS ]
I'M PRETTY SURE THE ONLY
ONE THAT THOUGHT
WE'RE DEFINITELY HITTIN'
BEDROCK WAS FRED HURT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I HAD MY WONDERS.
SO, NOW THAT WE'RE ON BEDROCK,
WE GOTTA GO UPSTREAM.
HOPEFULLY, WITH ANY LUCK,
THAT GOLD IS ALL
AROUND RIGHT THERE
AND WE'RE JUST GONNA FILL OUR
POCKETS WITH IT, ALL RIGHT?
-YEAH.
-YEAH, I THINK WE ARE, YEAH.
[ TRANQUIL TUNE PLAYS ]
THERE WAS TIMES WHEN EVERYONE
DOUBTED ME, EXCEPT FOR FRED.
OF ALL PEOPLE,
FRED'S THE ONE.
FRED'S THE ONE GONNA STAND
BY YOUR SIDE.
AS MUCH AS WE FIGHT,
FRED'S GONNA BE THE ONE
TO KEEP DIGGIN'.
[ LAUGHING ]
HE'S MY FATHER.
WHAT THE HELL?
DUSTIN GAVE ME
A BIG COMPLIMENT.
HE WAS SO PROUD OF THE FACT THAT
I, UH, DID A GOOD JOB TODAY.
I NEVER DOUBTED WE WOULD
GET TO THE BOTTOM.
WE'RE TOO PERSISTENT
TO GIVE UP.
OR ELSE, TOO DUMB.
I DON'T KNOW WHICH.
[ LAUGHING ]
♪♪
Narrator:
ON THE NEXT "GOLD RUSH:
WHITE WATER"...
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
Dustin:
I'd love to see a bunch
of gold in the rocks,
but there's none today, man.
Rich:
Hey, Dustin, [indistinct]
around here,
why don't you come look
at something?
Doesn't that look
like...?
Holy [bleep], Rich,
that's all gold.
That's gold,
isn't it?!
-WHOO!
-OH, MY [BLEEP]
FOUND NUGGETS, BOYS!
CHECK OUT THOSE
NUGGETS, DUDE!
YEAH! WHOO!