♪
Narrator: ON THE FINALE
OF "GOLD RUSH: WHITE WATER"...
Wes: THAT'S DEATH
WAITING TO HAPPEN.
-[BLEEP] [BLEEP]
-WHOA! HEY!
Narrator: ...AFTER TWO SEASONS
RISKING THEIR LIVES...
...DIVING FOR GOLD
IN RAGING McKINLEY CREEK...
-WATCH OUT!
-BRIDGE IS GONNA GO!
GET OUT!
YOU THOUGHT
YOUR JOB WAS HARD!
Narrator: ...THE DAKOTA BOYS
ARE NOW IN A RACE
TO BEAT THE ALASKAN WINTER.
Dustin: HEY, FRED, IF YOU FALL
OFF THAT, YOU'RE DONE.
Carlos: QUICK!
HYPOTHERMIA IS GONNA SET IN.
[BLEEP]
Narrator: AND THEY'RE ABOUT
TO FIND OUT
IF ALL THEIR EFFORTS WILL TURN
INTO A MONSTER PAY DAY.
[BLEEP]
IS JUST PILING UP, MAN.
LOOK AT THIS!
I'LL BE [BLEEP]
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
DISCOVERY COMMUNICATIONS
♪
-LOOK AT THAT [BLEEP]
-LOOK AT THE GOLD!
Narrator: AT McKINLEY CREEK,
THE DAKOTA BOYS HAVE FINALLY
DREDGED THE GOLD ON BEDROCK.
-[BLEEP]
-OH, MY [BLEEP]
THIS IS WHAT WE WERE
LOOKING FOR.
TIME TO MAKE SOME MONEY.
-LOOK! LOOK!
-HOLY [BLEEP]
-OH, MY!
Narrator: DUSTIN IS BANKING
ON A PAY DAY
THAT COULD MAKE THEM ALL RICH.
I DO LOVE MY JOB, BRO.
I LOVE MY JOB.
-[ LAUGHING ]
-LOOK AT THAT!
RIGHT HERE, RIGHT HERE.
Dustin:
WELL, WE GOT SOME GOLD, GUYS.
Narrator: THE FINAL GOLD WEIGH
FROM THE McKINLEY DIVE SITE.
Dustin: MOMENT OF TRUTH.
Narrator: DUSTIN HAS SHELLED OUT
OVER $75,000
TO RUN HIS OPERATION
FOR THE SEASON.
Dustin: 7, THAT'S 8.
Narrator:
BEFORE ANYONE GETS PAID,
HE NEEDS 60 OUNCES.
ONLY 10.3 OUNCES, GUYS.
[BLEEP]
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
THAT'S ALL THE GOLD DOWN THERE.
10.3 IS JUST [BLEEP]
THAT DON'T EVEN COVER
ALL OUR BILLS, DOES IT?
Dustin: NOT EVEN CLOSE.
I THOUGHT WE WERE GONNA WALK
AWAY WITH HUNDREDS OF OUNCES,
AND WE CAME OUT
WITH $13,000 WORTH OF GOLD.
REALLY NOT WORTH THE TIME
AND EFFORT THAT WE PUT IN.
10.3 OUNCES
FOR THE SEASON?
WE PUT IN A [BLEEP]
TON OF WORK
ON THAT AREA UP THERE.
WE'RE WASTING OUR TIME.
I WAS HOPING TO HAVE A FUTURE
FOR MY LITTLE GIRL,
YOU KNOW, SCHOOL, COLLEGE.
10.3 OUNCES
CAN'T EVEN BUY HER SCHOOL BOOKS.
I FEEL YOUR PAIN.
IT'S KILLING ME, TOO.
I GOT EVERYTHING INTO THIS.
I KNOW THERE'S GOLD
IN THIS CLAY.
WE JUST HIT THE WRONG SPOT.
BUT I STILL THINK THERE'S STILL
PLENTY OF GOLD
TO FIND DOWN THERE.
McKINLEY, WE WERE GETTING
INTO THAT CRACK.
I THINK
WE GOT ALL THE GOLD
WE'RE EVER GONNA
GET FROM THERE,
AND I THINK
WE FINISHED THAT HOLE.
IT'S TOO DEEP, TOO DANGEROUS.
SOMEBODY IS GONNA DIE
DOWN THERE.
I'M CALLING IT,
AND IF WE'RE GONNA HAVE ANOTHER
SEASON MINING,
WE NEED TO MOVE ON.
WE NEED TO PROVE THAT
THERE'S GOLD UP THERE.
I THINK IT'S TIME
TO GO TO CAHOON.
I WANT TO GO UP TO CAHOON,
AND I WANT TO TEST AND SEE
IF THERE IS GOLD FARTHER UP.
I THINK
THAT'S A MISTAKE.
WELL, IT'S REALLY
RISKING A LOT.
WELL, WE GOT TWO OPTIONS,
FRED.
WE COULD EITHER MOVE ON
AND TRY TO FIND SOME GOLD,
OR WE CAN QUIT.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
Wes: I CAN'T AFFORD
TO SPEND ANOTHER SEASON
LIVING ON FUMES.
I DON'T KNOW IF I EVEN
WANT TO COME BACK UP HERE.
IT'S...GOLD MINING
IS A GAMBLE.
THERE'S NO GUARANTEES.
YOU JUST GOT TO GET OUT THERE
AND TRY.
YOU GUYS, DO YOU WANT TO COME
UP TO CAHOON WITH ME?
♪
HELL.
ANOTHER SEASON RIGHT NOW
DOESN'T SEEM LIKE...
ANYBODY IS GONNA COME BACK.
I'LL HAVE TO TRY TO EARN
EVERYBODY'S TRUST AGAIN
SOMEWHERE.
I HAVE TO CONVINCE THEM,
OR TRY TO CONVINCE THEM
TO COME BACK OR FOLLOW ME
UP TO CAHOON
AND PROVE THAT
THERE'S GOLD UP THERE.
Narrator:
IN THE CHILCUAGUE MOUNTAINS,
MOST MINERS
COUNT THEMSELVES LUCKY
IF THE SEASON RUNS
FOR 120 DAYS.
NOW PROSPECTING THIS NEW SITE
WILL PUSH THE DAKOTA BOYS
DEEP INTO OVERTIME.
LET'S GO CHECK IT OUT, GUYS.
SEE WHAT YOU'RE GETTING US
INTO, RIGHT?
DUSTIN, YOU KNOW, HE'S MY SON.
I'M GONNA GO AHEAD
AND I'LL LOOK AT IT.
I'LL GIVE HIM SOME ADVICE
WHETHER HE LIKES IT OR NOT.
Paul:
THE DUG-OUTS ARE READY.
2-HOUR HIKE, IT'S NOT
GONNA BE FUN,
AND THIS BETTER BE WORTH IT.
Narrator: DUSTIN IS HEADING
TO HIS HIGHEST CLAIM
CLOSEST TO THE MOTHER LODE.
THREE WEEKS AGO,
DUSTIN AND PAUL DISCOVERED
A PERFECT GOLD CATCH
UP REMOTE CAHOON CREEK.
Paul: THERE'S A WATERFALL
RIGHT THERE.
A WATERFALL ON TOP
OF A WATERFALL.
THAT'S WHERE
WE NEED TO BE.
OVER THE PAST 120 YEARS,
44,000 OUNCES OF GOLD
WORTH OVER $50 MILLION HAVE BEEN
MINED IN THESE MOUNTAINS.
THE MOTHER LODE
HAS NEVER BEEN FOUND,
BUT THE TRAIL
OF DOCUMENTED GOLD STRIKES
ALL POINT TO CAHOON CREEK
AS THE SOURCE.
[BLEEP] GET DOWN THERE?
NOW HE HAS TO CONVINCE
HIS EXHAUSTED CREW
IT'S WORTH THE RISK.
-WE'RE MINING DOWN THERE?
-MM-HMM.
-THAT'S A HELL OF A DROP, DUDE.
-UGH.
Fred: WHAT, 250 FEET?
AT LEAST.
MAYBE 300.
-AT LEAST.
IT'S A PRETTY STEEP WALL,
PRETTY MUCH STRAIGHT DOWN,
WOULD NOT WANT TO SLIP
AND FALL FROM HERE.
THAT WOULD NOT BE SURVIVABLE.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THIS.
Dustin:
GUYS, WHEN WE GET DOWN THERE,
THERE'S A LOT OF LOOSE ROCK,
AND IF YOU STEP ON ANYTHING
SMOOTH, YOU'RE GONNA SLIP.
WATCH YOUR FOOTING.
TRY NOT TO KNOCK ANYTHING DOWN
ON TOP OF US.
Paul: AS LONG AS YOU PICKED
A SPOT THAT'S GOT GOLD IN IT
AND WE CAN GET TO IT,
IT'LL BE GOOD.
I HOPE THERE'S [BLEEP]
GOLD IN IT.
HOPEFULLY WE CAN GET SOME
GOOD FEEDBACK AND GET STARTED.
HERE WE GO.
HEY, FRED! IF YOU FALL OFF
THAT, YOU'RE DONE.
ONE SLIP
AND I'M 300 FEET AWAY.
SAYONARA.
JUMP ROCK!
THE COMMUTE IS SCARY, MAN.
WE HAVE TO FRICKING MOUNTAIN
GOAT ALL THE WAY DOWN HERE.
I MIGHT HAVE A GOATEE,
BUT I AIN'T NO GOAT.
♪
Dustin: THERE IT IS.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
THIS IS IT RIGHT HERE.
BEDROCK ON THREE SIDES AND IT
LOOKS LIKE IT CAN HOLD GOLD.
-YEAH!
-WOW!
-LOOK AT THAT!
-THAT'S BADASS!
Fred: HOLY COW!
THIS IS THE END
OF A GLACIER.
Paul: WE'VE GOT
A PLUNGE POOL HERE.
IT SEEMS TO ME LIKE IT WOULD
HAVE A GOOD CATCH RIGHT THERE.
IT'S GOT A SLIDE.
WE GOT THESE BIG-ASS BOULDERS
UP THERE.
THERE COULD BE SOME BIG-ASS GOLD
RIGHT DOWN IN HERE.
Dustin: I HOPE SO.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YOU GUYS DOWN TO TEST
THIS HOLE UP HERE?
-YUP.
-HELL YEAH.
I LIKE THAT NICE LITTLE
PLUNGE POOL.
THIS COULD BE ONE HELL
OF A GOLD CATCH.
I GOT TO ADMIT THAT IT DOES
LOOK GOOD RIGHT HERE.
Dustin: WHAT?!
FRED HURT SAID SOMEWHERE
I PICKED LOOKS GOOD.
I DIDN'T SAY IT WAS GONNA BE
EASY OR ANYTHING, BUT [BLEEP]
THAT DOES LOOK INCREDIBLE
HERE THOUGH.
SELDOM DO I AGREE WITH DUSTIN'S
METHODS OF DOING THINGS.
HE MUST BE LEARNING SOMETHING.
SO WHAT'S THE PLAN OF ACTION?
WE'RE GONNA CLEAN
THIS AREA OUT,
MOVE SOME OF THESE TREES
OUT OF THE WAY
AND THEN WE'LL DO SOME TESTS.
I'VE GOT TO GET MY DREDGE.
WE'RE GONNA DIG FOR A WEEK
OR TWO
AND SEE HOW MUCH GOLD
WE CAN GET.
Narrator: THIS PART OF THE CREEK
HAS ALL THE SIGNS
OF THE PERFECT GOLD CATCH --
A PLUNGE POOL IN THE BEDROCK,
WHICH IS FULL OF HEAVY BOULDERS.
DUSTIN WILL DREDGE A TEST HOLE
TO PROVE IT CONTAINS
ENOUGH GOLD
TO MAKE IT WORTH MINING.
DUSTIN, I ACTUALLY
AGREE WITH YOU.
I THINK THAT'S A GOOD,
SOLID PLAN.
FRED IS ON BOARD
WITH DUSTIN'S MINE PLAN,
BUT, AT 75 YEARS OLD,
MUST MAKE A TOUGH CALL.
I DON'T KNOW IF I'M GONNA BE
ABLE TO MAKE IT
BACK DOWN HERE AGAIN.
IT'S JUST
A HARD MOUNTAIN CLIMB.
IT'S TOO
PHYSICALLY DEMANDING.
Dustin: YOU SURE YOU DON'T WANT
TO JOIN US ON THIS, MAN?
-EH.
-THIS IS GONNA BE EPIC.
I'M NOT GONNA BE ABLE TO GET
BACK UP THESE WALLS, MAN.
THEY DON'T HAVE...
-NOT WITH THAT ATTITUDE.
Y'ALL ARE GONNA HAVE
TO GET A LITTER
AND PULL ME UP
THE DAMN HILL.
SEE YOU LATER.
I GOT TO GO.
Fred: I DON'T THINK
A 75-YEAR-OLD MAN
NEED TO BE RUNNING DOWN
THE DAMN HILLS THAT STEEP,
BUT I SURE WISH THEM LUCK.
Dustin: ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
WE CAN'T WORK
WITH THIS OVER OUR HEAD.
I MEAN, IT'S LIKE LOOMING DEATH.
DRAG THEM OUT.
CUT THEM UP AND THROW THEM
OVER THE EDGE.
Wes: WELL, LET'S SEE
ABOUT GETTING OUR CAP STAND
TO GET IT SET UP.
-ALL RIGHT.
CAP STAND AND A CHAIN SAW,
LET'S GO GET IT, MAN.
YEAH.
Narrator: THE LOGS COULD WASH
DOWN WITHOUT WARNING
AND CRUSH ANYONE CAUGHT
IN THEIR PATH.
TO REMOVE THESE WIDOWMAKERS,
THE CREW HAS JUST A CHAIN SAW
AND A SMALL PORTABLE WINCH.
THIS LITTLE WINCH JUST TO
PULL THESE LOGS OUT...
IT'S CAPABLE OF PULLING, LIKE,
A TON AND A HALF ALMOST,
SO IT SHOULD HAVE THE POWER
TO PULL THESE OUT.
SO THIS THING IS BURIED
A LITTLE BIT ON THE END.
LET'S SEE WHAT THIS LITTLE GUY
HAS GOT, MAN.
[ ENGINE STARTS ]
WHOO.
COME ON.
YOU CAN DO IT.
GET THAT [BLEEP]
THERE IT GOES.
-YEAH!
THAT'S WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
Dustin: WATCH YOURSELVES.
SPLASH ZONE!
WE GOT THE FIRST ONE DOWN,
ANOTHER HALF DOZEN TO GO.
NEXT!
HEY, HEY!
GET OVER HERE.
Paul: THESE CANYON WALLS
ARE SO STEEP
THAT ANYTHING
COULD HAPPEN.
WE'RE OUT IN THE MIDDLE
OF NOWHERE.
IT'S NOT EASY TO GET ANYBODY
OUT OF THIS SPOT
TO GET THEM TO SAFETY.
THIS IS NOT A GOOD SPOT
TO GET HURT AT.
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT'S NEXT?
Paul: REALLY GOT THAT ONE
BAD HANGER RIGHT THERE.
ONCE WE GET THAT ONE OUT OF
THE WAY, I THINK WE'VE GOT IT.
ALL RIGHT.
READY TO GO.
LET'S GO LOOK AT THE ROOT WAD
AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
♪
STUPID, STUPID.
WOO-HOO-HOO!
I'VE ONLY GOT ONE HAND.
I AIN'T [BLEEP] LETTING GO.
COPY.
GET THE HELL
OUT OF THERE.
YIPPEE!
[ ENGINE STARTS ]
COME ON!
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE THERE
ANYMORE.
IT'S LOCKED IN TIGHT.
WELL, IT'S ALMOST 5:00.
LET'S GET THIS DONE.
Paul: THE ONLY THING
WE MIGHT BE ABLE TO DO NOW
IS TO HANG OFF A ROPE
AND CUT THAT [BLEEP] THING.
I REALLY DON'T WANT TO CUT IT.
[BLEEP] SCARES ME.
BRING ME THE CHAIN SAW.
LET'S GET [BLEEP] STUPID.
♪
IT'S A LITTLE BIT SKETCHY FOR ME
RIGHT HERE.
YOU WANT THE BRAKE ON?
♪
Wes: [BLEEP]
THAT'S DEATH
WAITING TO HAPPEN.
OH [BLEEP] WHOA!
-HEY!
THAT'S A SLIPPERY
[BLEEP] BOY.
WHEW.
♪
OKAY.
TRY THAT.
SEE IF YOU BREAK IT.
♪
IT'S GOING!
-YEAH!
-WOO-HOO!
Paul: THE THINGS WE DO
FOR GOLD.
WHEW.
YOU EVER SIT AROUND AND ASK
WHY YOU DO THE [BLEEP]
YOU DO?
ALL THE TIME.
I DO.
LET'S GET
THE HELL OUT OF HERE.
THIS HOLE IS READY TO GO.
YEAH.
♪
Dustin: AIN'T MUCH TIME, MAN.
Narrator: HIGH IN THE CHILCUAGUE
MOUNTAINS AT CAHOON CREEK,
DUSTIN IS ATTEMPTING
TO DREDGE A TEST HOLE
AND PROVE THERE'S ENOUGH GOLD
TO MAKE IT WORTH MINING
BEFORE THE ALASKAN WINTER
SHUTS THEM DOWN.
I'M EXCITED TO GET
DOWN THERE, MAN.
THERE COULD BE A LOT OF GOLD.
Narrator:
TO SET UP HIS NEW SITE,
DUSTIN HAS TO REINVEST 2 OUNCES
OF HIS MEAGER McKINLEY GOLD
TO COVER A $2,500 HELI LIFT.
TODAY IS KIND OF A PIVOTAL POINT
TO SEE IF WE'RE GONNA BE
ABLE TO MOVE ON
TO THE NEXT SITE OR NOT.
ONE OF MY BIG WORRIES,
CAHOON IS A LITTLE TIGHT.
THE DREDGE WON'T FIT,
OR WE SMASH IT UP.
IF THAT HAPPENS, THEN THERE'S
REALLY NOTHING I CAN DO.
Narrator: FROM THEIR OLD DIVE
SITE AT McKINLEY CREEK,
IT'S A 3/4-MILE FLIGHT UPSTREAM
TO WHERE IT MEETS CAHOON
AND THEN ANOTHER QUARTER MILE
INTO A CANYON SO NARROW
THE ONLY WAY TO GET THE DREDGE
IN IS USING A LONGLINE.
IT'S A VERY, VERY TIGHT CANYON
WE'RE TRYING TO GET
THIS DREDGE INTO.
YOU KNOW, IF WE USE
LITTLE EAGLE NELL,
WE'RE NOT GONNA GET TO GET
ANYTHING ELSE
DONE THIS YEAR AT ALL.
Carlos: YEAH, THAT'S GOOD.
THERE SHE IS.
Wes: I HEAR HER COMING.
ALL RIGHT. GET READY.
I'M READY.
Narrator:
BUSH PILOT MARY WILCOCK
IS A LONGLINE SPECIALIST.
-THERE YOU GO.
-THERE WE GO.
-IT'S GONNA BE RIGHT TO YOU.
-YUP. I GOT IT, GOT IT.
Carlos: OKAY.
UP, UP, UP!
THAT'S ALL MARY.
COME ON, MARY!
WOO-HOO!
Dustin: THERE GOES OUR FUTURE
RIGHT THERE.
BE SAFE WITH IT!
♪
GO!
HELLO, MARY.
IT'S GONNA BE A LITTLE TIGHT,
SO WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO
IS WE'RE GONNA SET IT
RIGHT NEXT
TO THE BARREL ON THE WATER SIDE
AND SLIDE IT IN.
♪
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
HEY, MAN. SHE'S GETTING
CLOSE TO THAT TREE.
HEY, LOOK OUT FOR THAT TREE.
♪
IS SHE GONNA BE ABLE
TO DO IT?
I DIDN'T HEAR HER RESPONSE.
WHERE'S SHE GOING, MAN?
I THINK
SHE'S TAKING IT BACK.
THAT'S [BLEEP] UP, MAN.
♪
WELL, IF SHE CAN'T DROP
THE THING IN HERE,
MY SEASON IS DONE.
YEAH!
Narrator: MARY RETURNS WITH THE
LONGLINE EXTENDED TO 200 FEET.
IT SHOULD KEEP HER FROM CRASHING
INTO THE TIGHT CANYON WALLS.
♪
BEAUTIFUL, BEAUTIFUL.
PERFECT.
THANK YOU FOR THAT.
OH, MAN.
IT FIT LIKE A DAMN GLOVE.
EVERYTHING IS SET UP
PERFECTLY DOWN HERE.
WHOO!
DAMN.
IT'S IN.
YOO-HOO-YOO!
♪
DUSTIN HAS MADE THE DECISION
TO GO UP TO CAHOON.
HE DIDN'T QUIT McKINLEY.
McKINLEY, TO ME, STILL HAS
A GREAT AMOUNT OF GOLD IN IT.
Narrator: TWO DAYS AGO,
DUSTIN SHUT DOWN
THEIR OLD DIVE SITE
ON McKINLEY CREEK,
BUT FRED IS BACK,
AND HE'S ROPED IN RICH
FOR ONE LAST SHOT
AT HITTING SOME BIG NUGGETS.
Fred: HEY, WE HAD 10 OUNCES
COME OUT OF THAT CRACK,
THE MOST WE'VE GOT
OUT OF TWO SEASONS.
I PERSONALLY THINK WE LEFT
A LITTLE BIT BEHIND.
Narrator:
TO ACCESS ANY REMAINING GOLD
LEFT IN THE NARROW NUGGET TRAP,
FRED HAS MacGYVERED
HIS OWN TOOL.
SO WHAT I DID, I JUST...
I RAN OVER IT WITH THE LOADER
DOWN AT PORCUPINE
AND SMASHED IT DOWN,
AND IT STAYED.
WE'RE GONNA CALL THAT
OUR CREVICE CLEANER.
Narrator:
THE 6-INCH NOZZLE WAS TOO WIDE
TO GET INTO THE CRACK.
FRED'S 3-INCH CREVICE CLEANER
SHOULD SUCK UP
ANY REMAINING GOLD.
Fred: SO WE GOT OUR
VACUUM-CLEANER ATTACHMENT
ALL FIXED UP.
WHATEVER IS LEFT,
I'M GONNA GO GET IT.
[ ENGINE STARTS ]
Rich: ALL RIGHT, FRED, WELL,
YOU HAVE A SAFE DIVE.
BE CAREFUL.
-ALL RIGHT.
IT'S A LONG WAY DOWN.
Narrator: THE NUGGET TRAP IS
RIGHT AT THE BOTTOM
OF THE DREDGED-OUT HOLE BENEATH
AN UNSTABLE 18-FOOT WALL.
FRED!
FRED, YOU COPY?
COPY.
MAYBE THERE'S SOME
BIG GOLD IN THERE, FRED.
Fred: I'M LOOKING
FOR BIG [BLEEP]
IF IT'S GOT GOLD IN THERE,
IT'S GONNA BE
ON THE TOP OF THAT STUFF.
I JUST DON'T SEE REAL BIG,
GIANT NUGGETS
HANGING AROUND IN THERE.
YOU'RE NOT SEEING ANY STUFF
IN THERE LIKE THAT.
I DIDN'T SEE ANY [BLEEP]
ALL RIGHT.
YOU CAN SEE THAT IT'S BEEN
DREDGED OUT
AND DREDGED OUT
REALLY CLEAN.
JUST CAME DOWN TO NOTHING.
THEY GOT EVERYTHING CLEANED
OUT IN THAT CREVICE.
DUSTIN WAS RIGHT.
Narrator: UP AHEAD...
Fred: THAT MEANS WE'RE GETTING
A LITTLE CLOSER
TO THE SOURCE.
THIS COULD DEFINITELY BE
THE DIG THAT CHANGES OUR WORLD.
Man: THAT IS
SOME CHUNKY GOLD.
Carlos: [BLEEP] QUICK!
HYPOTHERMIA IS GONNA SET IN.
Woman on radio: BRINGING YOU THE
WEATHER FORECAST FOR HAINES.
UP NEAR THE BORDER,
THE MOUNTAINTOPS
GOT THEIR FIRST
DUSTING OF THE WHITE STUFF,
AND WITH THE COLD FRONT
SET TO MOVE IN
OVER THE NEXT FEW DAYS,
THERE'S POTENTIAL
FOR SNOW IN TOWN.
Dustin: GETTING LATE [BLEEP]
Narrator: UP REMOTE CAHOON CREEK
WITH TEMPERATURES
PLUNGING TOWARDS
THE FREEZING POINT,
DUSTIN IS ATTEMPTING
TO DREDGE A TEST HOLE
AND PROVE TO HIS CREW
THERE'S ENOUGH GOLD
TO MAKE A PROFIT MINING IT.
-PAUL!
-YEP?
LET'S SEE WHAT WE CAN FIND, MAN.
IT'S TIME TO DIG UP CAHOON,
FIND OUT IF THERE'S
ANY GOLD DOWN THERE.
FIRST ONE TO DIVE IN CAHOON!
IT'S LIKE DIVING
IN A SWIMMING POOL,
OTHER THAN IT'S 34 DEGREES.
Narrator: THE WATER IN CAHOON
FEEDS STRAIGHT OFF A GLACIER.
THE DIVERS' HOT-WATER SYSTEM
IS ALL THAT STANDS
BETWEEN PAUL
AND LETHAL HYPOTHERMIA.
THE WATER IS NOT
VERY HOT, MAN.
YOU'RE ABOUT
TO TAKE THIS?
SO FIRST, LET'S TRY TO GET
THE LUMBER OUT.
I WOULD LOVE TO GET
THIS SUCKER OUT
SO I COULD SHOOT
THROUGH THERE.
SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN.
HOPEFULLY THERE'S
SOME GOLD THERE
SO THIS MAKES THIS
ALL WORTH IT.
Rich: THIS WATER IS SO HARD
TO HEAT, MAN.
-IT'S SO COLD.
-IT'S SO HARD TO HEAT.
WE'RE REALLY AT THE LIMITATIONS
OF OUR HEATERS.
THIS IS GONNA BE
THE HARDEST PART OF OUR SEASON.
YEAH.
HERE, MAN.
WE GOT TO HOOK UP THE AIR.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M READY.
AH!
Dustin: THERE HAS TO BE PROOF
THAT THERE'S GOLD DOWN THERE.
WE NEED TO KNOW THAT WE'RE
COMING BACK FOR A GOOD REASON.
WHAT WE HAVE RIGHT NOW
IS A TREE WITH LIMBS,
AND IT'S MESSING UP
OUR PROGRAM.
THERE COULD BE A LOT
OF GOLD DOWN THERE, MAN.
SO WE GOT TO GET IT
OUT OF THERE.
Wes: YEAH.
OKAY.
LET'S DO THAT FIRST.
Narrator: THE TREES HAVE BEEN
POUNDED INTO PLACE,
LOCKED IN
WITH BOULDERS AND DIRT.
THEY'RE BLOCKING THE MINERS
FROM A POCKET OF GOLD
ON THE BEDROCK
THAT COULD BE WORTH MILLIONS.
WOO-HOO!
IT FEELS GOOD!
WELL, I USUALLY DON'T SAY THIS,
BUT, PAUL,
IT'S TIME TO TUNNEL DOWN
AS FAR AS YOU CAN GO, MAN.
[ LAUGHS ]
WE'RE PLAYING A WHOLE
NEW GAME, BABY,
A WHOLE NEW GAME.
ALL RIGHT.
PAUL, YOU GET ENOUGH HOT WATER?
HERE WE GO.
[ SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ]
THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
PULL ON IT!
NOPE.
SHE AIN'T COMING LOOSE.
ALL RIGHT.
BACK OFF ON HER.
IT AIN'T MOVING.
IT'S 4:42 OR 3 OR SO,
SO IT'S A QUARTER
TO FIVE RIGHT NOW.
I'M GONNA TELL YOU
STRAIGHT UP THAT
YOU PROBABLY SHOULDN'T STAY
IN THAT LONG, MAN.
Paul: OKAY.
Narrator: TO GET OUT OF THE
REMOTE CAHOON DIVE SITE
REQUIRES A 200-FOOT ASSENT.
DUSTIN HAS SET
A 5:00 P.M. CUTOFF
TO AVOID THE DANGEROUS
CLIMB IN DARKNESS.
Dustin: WE STILL HAVE TWO HOURS
TO HIKE OUT OF HERE.
WE'RE IN THE BOTTOM
OF A 200-FOOT CLIFF,
PRETTY MUCH DEATH
AROUND EVERY CORNER.
GOOD JOB, BUDDY.
Carlos: GOOD DIVE, PAUL.
GOOD DIVE.
GOOD JOB.
YOU COLD?
LEAVE 'EM RUNNING.
LET HIM WARM UP!
WHAT DO YOU THINK, MAN?
THE ONE
WE'RE TRYING TO PULL,
THERE'S ANOTHER ONE
RIGHT THERE.
THERE'S TWO MORE GOING
STRAIGHT DOWN.
Carlos: HOLY [BLEEP]
RIGHT THERE.
-WHAT'S THAT?
-IT'S A [BLEEP] PIECE OF GOLD.
-OH [BLEEP]
-YEAH!
-OH, YEAH, DUDE!
-LOOK AT IT! THAT'S...
OOH, YEAH!
Dustin:
THERE'S GOLD IN HERE, MAN.
HOLY [BLEEP]
THAT'S GOLD, MAN.
ON THE TOP, MAN
[BLEEP]
-YEAH.
-THAT'S CRAZY.
IF WE'RE GETTING THIS
CHUNKY STUFF UP TOP,
THERE'S GOT TO BE
SOME NUGGETS DOWN THERE.
YEAH!
♪
TEMPERATURES TOOK
A STEEP DIVE OVERNIGHT
AND ARE CONTINUING TO DROP.
AS THE SNOW LINE
MOVES DOWN THE MOUNTAINS,
WE'RE GONNA SEE SNOW
FALLING AT ANYTHING
ABOUT 1,000 FEET REAL SOON.
Dustin: WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO KEEP
A REALLY CLOSE EYE
ON THIS WEATHER.
BECAUSE ALL IT'S GONNA
TAKE IT ONE SNOWFALL,
AND WE WON'T EVEN GET
OUR EQUIPMENT OUT OF THERE.
Fred:
IT'S JUST GONNA HAPPEN.
WELL, I DON'T WANT IT TO.
IT'S GONNA.
I MEAN, WE BEEN
PUSHING OUR LUCK.
IT SHOULD'VE ALREADY
SNOWED UP HERE USUALLY,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
YOU COULDN'T GET CAUGHT
IN A FEROCIOUS SNOWSTORM
UP HERE AT ANY TIME.
AND I UNDERSTAND THAT.
WHETHER WE GET INTO THE BOTTOM
OF THIS THING
BEFORE THAT HAPPENS
IS UP TO US.
I'VE DONE AMAZING THINGS
IN MY LIFE
BECAUSE I'VE BEEN TOLD
IT'S TOO HARD.
IT'S SCARY.
IT'S HOPELESS, AND I'VE BEEN
TOLD THIS MY WHOLE LIFE.
IT ONLY MOTIVATES ME
TO PUSH HARDER.
I'M GONNA DIG IT OUT.
Narrator: DUSTIN NEEDS TO DREDGE
A TEST HOLE
AND PROVE TO HIMSELF
AND HIS CREW
THAT THERE'S ENOUGH GOLD
IN CAHOON CREEK
TO MAKE IT WORTH MINING,
BUT HE'S RACING AGAINST
THE ALASKAN WINTER.
IT'S TIME FOR ME
TO GET SUITED UP.
I'M GONNA PUT A REALLY
LONG DAY IN.
WE'RE GONNA GET RICH,
GET AS MUCH HOT WATER
AS WE CAN GET TO STAY DOWN
AS LONG AS WE CAN.
IT COULD BE OUR LAST CHANCE.
Rich:
THE WATER UP HERE ON CAHOON,
I THINK IT'S IN THE LOW 30s
AT THE WARMEST.
IF WE CAN'T GET ENOUGH
HOT WATER, WE CAN'T DIVE,
SO WHAT I'M GONNA DO IS
I'M GONNA PUT A VALVE
AND GIVE THE WATER JUST
A LITTLE MORE TIME TO HEAT UP
BEFORE IT GOES UP TO OUR DIVER.
Narrator: RICH'S PLAN --
INSTALL A VALVE
TO SLOW DOWN THE FLOW OF WATER,
KEEPING IT IN
THE HEATING CHAMBER LONGER,
WHICH SHOULD INCREASE
THE TEMPERATURE
OF THE DIVER'S WATER SUPPLY.
Rich: THIS IS ABOUT
AS MUCH AS I GOT.
Dustin: ALL RIGHT.
[BLEEP] LET'S DO IT!
♪
ALL RIGHT.
Narrator:
IN THE FIRST CAHOON DIVE,
PAUL DREDGED UP A GOLD FLAKE
FROM NEAR THE SURFACE...
...BUT LOGS JAMMED
IN THE CREEK BED
HAVE STOPPED ALL DREDGING.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
I KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW HOW IN THE HELL
WE'RE GONNA DO IT, MAN.
IT'S GONNA TAKE
SOME BREAKING WORK, BRO.
HERE WE GO AGAIN.
♪
COME ON!
DUDE!
PULL.
WOO-HOO!
[BLEEP] YEAH!
THAT'S AWESOME!
WOO-HOO!
ONE THING, MAN,
ALASKA HAS TAUGHT ME,
IF THERE'S A WILL,
THERE'S A FRICKING WAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
THERE MIGHT BE GOLD
UNDER THAT TREE, MAN.
Narrator: THE LOGS CLEAR,
DUSTIN CAN DREDGE A TEST HOLE
STRAIGHT DOWN,
SENDING 6 YARDS OF PAY DIRT
AN HOUR ACROSS THE SLUICE.
FOR THIS PLUNGE POOL
TO BE WORTH DREDGING,
THEY MUST MINE AT LEAST
HALF AN OUNCE A DAY.
UGH!
[BLEEP]
HOLY.
DUSTIN,
THE HOT WATER BLEW OFF.
QUICK.
HYPOTHERMIA IS GONNA SET IN.
OH [BLEEP]
Narrator:
AT CAHOON CREEK IN ALASKA
WEIGHING UP HIS CAREER CHOICE --
CARLOS MINOR.
GOLD, UNION JOB,
GOLD, UNION JOB.
RAT RACE FOREVER,
9 TO 5
UNTIL THE DAY YOU DIE,
ALASKA, COLD, COLD,
ALASKA, ALASKA, DANGER, DANGER,
ADVENTURE,
POSSIBLY MILLIONAIRE.
♪
Dustin: BOY, THAT WATER FEELS
GOOD WHEN IT COMES OUT.
Narrator:
DIVING IN SUBZERO TEMPERATURES,
DUSTIN'S HOT-WATER LINE
DETACHED FROM HIS SUIT,
REMOVING HIS ONLY DEFENSE
FROM LIFE-THREATENING COLD.
Carlos: WHAT DO YOU
THINK, BRO?
CALL IT, EVACUATE, MAN,
BEFORE THINGS GET MORE CRAZY
AND SEE WHAT WE GOT?
Dustin:
I'M JUST GETTING STARTED, MAN.
I NEED MORE DIRT
THROUGH THE BOX.
ALL RIGHT.
-LET'S DO IT.
Narrator: WITH THE BIG FREEZE
ABOUT TO HIT,
TIME IS RUNNING OUT FOR DUSTIN
TO PROVE THIS PLUNGE POOL
IS RICH IN GOLD.
Dustin: OW.
DUDE, WE'RE DOWN DEEP
IN THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE.
NOT IN THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE,
DOWN DEEP
IN THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE.
IF HE GOES INTO HYPOTHERMIA
AND HE PASSES OUT,
THERE'S NO 911
COMING RIGHT DOWN THE ROAD.
ANYTHING HAPPENS RIGHT NOW,
WE CAN'T GET HIM OUT OF HERE
FAST ENOUGH, DUDE.
♪
FRICKING RAIN.
Dustin: HOLD ON.
Carlos:
IF IT STARTS RAINING HARDER,
IT MAKES IT MORE DANGEROUS.
WE'RE SUCH IN A NARROW VALLEY,
IT WON'T COME UP
A COUPLE OF INCHES.
IT'S GONNA COME UP
A COUPLE OF FEET.
Dustin: [BLEEP]
AH.
Carlos:
WHAT DO YOU DO, MAN?
WHAT DO YOU DO?
ALL RIGHT.
IT'S STARTING
TO GET REALLY CRAZY.
LET'S BAIL OUT OF HERE, MAN.
PULL THE MATS, MAN.
TIME TO FIND OUT
WHAT'S IN THERE.
HOPEFULLY WE FIND ENOUGH
TO COME BACK NEXT SEASON.
Narrator: DUSTIN HAS CALLED TIME
ON THE MINING.
BEFORE HEADING SOUTH,
THE DAKOTA BOYS PACK UP CAMP
FOR WHAT COULD BE
THE LAST TIME.
Paul:
TRYING TO GET THINGS CLOSED UP
SO WE CAN GET OUT OF HERE
BEFORE IT FREEZES.
Narrator:
RICH CLEANS UP THE CONCENTRATE
FROM WHAT ADDS UP
TO JUST SIX HOURS DREDGING.
Rich: JUST...I'VE NEVER SEEN
MATERIAL LIKE THIS,
A LOT OF GRANITE,
A LOT OF BLACK SAND.
SO NOW WE JUST GOT TO PAN IT OUT
AND FIND OUT WHAT WE'VE GOT.
Narrator: TO MAKE IT WORTH
MINING NEXT SEASON,
THEY WOULD NEED MORE
THAN HALF AN OUNCE.
Rich: OH, MY GOODNESS.
NO, WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE BOULDERS.
DUSTIN, LOOK AT THIS, BUD.
WHEN HAVE YOU EVER
BASICALLY DONE A TEST HOLE...
-YEAH.
-...AND SEEN THAT KIND OF GOLD?
OH, MY [BLEEP]
Dustin:
THERE'S PROBABLY AN OUNCE,
OUNCE AND A HALF OF GOLD
HERE MAYBE.
SIX FRICKING HOURS
OF DIVING, DUDE.
WOW.
Narrator:
OVER $1,000 WORTH OF GOLD
FROM HALF A DAY'S DREDGING
MAKES CAHOON CREEK
THE BEST GROUND
THE DAKOTA BOYS HAVE EVER MINED.
-EASY, FRED.
-DOGGONE. WOW!
HEY, MAYBE WE'RE GETTING
A LITTLE CLOSER TO THE SOURCE,
WHEREVER THE HELL
THAT IS.
THAT'S WHAT'S GOING ON.
WE'RE BUTT-UP AGAINST IT.
I THINK WE'RE REAL CLOSE
TO WHEREVER IT STARTS.
Paul: IF WE'RE GETTING THIS
CHUNKY STUFF UP TOP,
WHAT HAVE WE
LEFT BEHIND RIGHT NOW?
THAT'S WHAT KEEPS
GOING THROUGH MY MIND.
THIS COULD BE THE SPOT
THAT CHANGES EVERYTHING.
I KNOW I SAID
THAT ABOUT McKINLEY.
I WAS WRONG ABOUT THAT, BUT NOW
WE KNOW THERE'S GOLD HIGHER UP.
IT'S JUST THERE FOR US
TO GO GET.
I'M GONNA WORK
ALL WINTER LONG,
AND I'M GONNA MAKE ENOUGH
MONEY TO RUN THIS OPERATION
FOR ANOTHER SEASON,
AND I REALLY HOPE...
I REALLY HOPE THAT YOU GUYS
WILL STICK WITH ME.
ARE YOU GUYS IN?
-AFTER SEEING THAT, YEAH.
-YEAH.
IT'S THE FIRST TIME
WE'VE EVER SEEN GOLD LIKE THAT.
I MEAN, WE'VE BEEN HITTING IT
HARD FOR THE PAST 2 SEASONS,
AND WE'VE NEVER DONE
THIS GOOD EVER.
Wes: IF WE DIDN'T COME BACK
AND WE PASS THIS UP,
WE'D REGRET IT
THE REST OF OUR LIFE.
-YEP.
-WE WOULD.
THAT'S GOOD GOLD,
GOOD GOLD.
WHO'S CAHOON HUNGRY, MAN?
WHO'S CAHOON HUNGRY NOW?
I'M GONNA BE BACK UP HERE
NEXT YEAR.
Dustin: WE KNOW
WHERE IT'S AT NOW.
THIS COULD DEFINITELY BE THE DIG
THAT CHANGES OUR WORLD.
YEAH.
Narrator: THE DAKOTA BOYS GO
BACK TO THEIR DAY JOBS
SO THAT IN SIX MONTHS,
THEY CAN RETURN FOR ANOTHER
CHANCE AT STRIKING IT RICH.
ON THE NEXT SPECIAL EPISODE
OF "GOLD RUSH: WHITE WATER"...
WHAT DO YOU GUYS WANT FROM ME?
Narrator:
...THE MINERS REVEAL ALL.
WHAT YOU DIDN'T SEE...
I WENT OFF ON MY OWN EXPEDITION.
-BUDDY, WE GOT GOLD.
-UH-HUH.
FRED TRIED TO RUN
A MUTINY ON ME.
WHAT KIND OF [BLEEP]
MEN ARE YOU?
GET IT OFF!
[BLEEP]
I HAD NIGHTMARES
FOR A COUPLE MONTHS.
Carlos: YOU LOST A MARINE,
YOU LOST A MAN,
AND YOU PAID FOR IT.
I DON'T THINK HIS LIFE
WILL EVER BE THE SAME AGAIN.