♪♪
I'M IN THE WATER TODAY.
IT'S ALWAYS A CHALLENGE,
BROTHER.
ALWAYS A CHALLENGE.
I'M A DIVER MAN.
YOU CAN'T KEEP ME
OUT OF THE WATER, NO.
HELL NO, THAT'S MY JOB, MAN.
THAT'S WHAT I DO.
THAT'S WHO I AM.
TONS OF GOLD, MAN.
THAT'S WHAT I'M THINKING.
YOU KNOW.
[ LAUGHS ] GOLD, BROTHER.
FEEL IT UP!
I GOT A FAMILY TO SUPPORT.
I GOT A FAMILY TO
GO HOME TO SO,
IT MAKES ME WANNA STAY
MORE ALIVE THAN USUAL.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
IT MAKES ME WANNA
FIGHT FOR MY LIFE.
KEEP THAT MASK
DRY, DRY, DRY MAN.
DRY, DRY, DRY.
THIS IS THE ONLY SKILL
I KNOW WHAT TO DO.
DIVE AND PROVIDE FOR MY FAMILY.
WE'RE TIRED OF LETTING
MOTHER NATURE WIN.
IT'S TIME TO FIGHT BACK.
[ GRUNTS ]
WHOA, FRED, STOP!
YEAH, I SEE WHAT'S GOING ON.
COME ON, NOW, GIVE ME A BREAK.
[ BLEEP ] [ BLEEP ]
MIKE, KEEP IT OUT OF THE WATER.
♪♪
I'D LOVE TO PULL UP
A BUCKET OF GOLD.
I'D LOVE TO JUST HIT IT BIG.
ALWAYS BIG.
[ LAUGHS ]
NOW WE'RE GETTING
INTO GOLD, BABY!
-WOW.
-OH, MAN.
THIS IS A GOOD SIGN.
♪♪
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
DISCOVERY COMMUNICATIONS
♪♪
WOW, THAT IS
A LOT OF DAMN WATER.
OH, MAN.
WHOO, IT LOOKS
HORRIBLE RIGHT NOW.
Narrator: HIGH IN ALASKA'S
CHILKAT MOUNTAINS,
THE DAKOTA BOYS ARE ON
THE HUNT FOR A GOLD DEPOSIT
THAT WILL CHANGE THEIR LIVES.
♪♪
THIS IS A FIGHT
WITH MOTHER NATURE.
SUN CAME OUT ON TOP
OF THE MOUNTAINS
AND THIS IS ALL SNOW MELT.
JUST ABOUT AS BAD AS
THIS WATER CAN GET
OUTSIDE OF BEING A FLOOD.
MOTHER NATURE'S TRYING
TO GET RID OF THAT ICE.
THIS IS THE RESULT RIGHT HERE.
♪♪
Narrator: GLACIAL MELT HAS
SWOLLEN THE CREEK
TO A FLOW OF 1,000 TONS
OF WATER A MINUTE
THAT WILL PUMMEL THEIR
BODIES AS THEY DIVE.
Dustin: SO I PICKED THE WORST
SPOT IN THE WORLD
TO DIG FOR GOLD.
WHEN THE SUN COMES OUT,
THE WATER GOES UP.
THIS IS WHAT
IT'S LIKE DIGGING OUT HERE.
Narrator: ALMOST HALFWAY
THROUGH THE SEASON,
THEY'VE FOUND JUST ONE
OUNCE OF GOLD WORTH $1,200.
Dustin: I KNOW THERE'S GOLD.
JUST OUT OF REACH RIGHT NOW,
BUT I'M-A GET TO IT.
♪♪
Narrator: THE ALASKAN MINING
SEASON IS SO SHORT,
THEY CAN'T AFFORD TO WAIT
FOR THE WATER TO CALM DOWN.
♪♪
Dustin: I AM IN A HURRY.
I'M $75,000 IN DEBT.
AND IF I DON'T GET
DOWN THERE TO GOLD,
THE McKINLEY DREAM IS OVER.
I AM IN SUCH A POSITION
TO WHERE I'M JUST
HEMORRHAGING MONEY ON THIS.
IT'S TAKEN,
IN MY OPINION, FOREVER.
♪♪
Narrator:
PROFESSIONAL DIVER CARLOS MINOR
IS DIVING TODAY.
I'M IN THE WATER TODAY.
THAT'S BAD NEWS.
Narrator: ALONGSIDE
NEW GUY, RICH WEBSTER.
THERE'S SO MUCH
CURRENT RIGHT NOW.
SO WE GOTTA REALLY BE
ON OUR GAME TODAY.
CARLOS, WE'RE GOING TO
THE FREAKING GUT OF THAT BEAST.
YEAH, BROTHER.
YOU AND I ARE GONNA BE
TEARING THIS UP IN HERE.
Carlos: THIS IS WHAT WE'RE
MADE OUT OF, MAN.
YOU CAN MAKE A BETTER
LIFE FOR YOURSELF,
WHY WOULDN'T IT BE WORTH IT?
THIS IS HOW I GET A PAYCHECK.
THIS IS NOT RECREATIONAL
FOR ME, MAN.
I MEAN THIS IS MY JOB.
OOH, DOGGY.
WHAT COULD BE DOWN THERE,
IT COULD BE LIFE CHANGING
FOR ALL OF US.
TO WHERE NONE OF US
EVER HAVE TO WORK AGAIN.
YOU TWO ARE GOING DOWN IF YOU'RE
COMFORTABLE WITH THIS WATER.
IF YOU'RE NOT,
I'LL DO IT FOR YOU.
-NO, NO.
-AH, WHAT A CHALLENGE, MAN.
[ LAUGHTER ]
Dustin:
I'M GONNA BE ON COMMS TODAY.
LET'S REALLY COMMUNICATE.
I THINK EVERYTHING'S
AS SAFE AS WE CAN MAKE IT.
DON'T LET YOUR
SLACK GO UNDERNEATH.
SO WHEN HE GETS
UP AND WALKS BACK,
YOU HAVE TO SAY,
"I'M COMING UP."
YOU'RE JUST GONNA
HAVE TO BE ON POINT. GET IT?
IF YOU HEAR DIVER UP,
EVERYBODY'S UP AND OUT.
WELL, LET'S SEE
WHAT HAPPENS, MAN.
THE FLOW OF THE WATER IS ABOUT
TWICE AS FAST AS NORMAL.
BAD NEWS.
WELL, GOOD LUCK GUYS.
SO EVERYBODY BE SAFE,
ALL RIGHT?
YOU HAVE TO GO COWBOY IN
ALASKA, MAN, YOU KNOW,
'CAUSE IT DOESN'T
PLAY BY YOUR RULES.
BAD MEDICINE IF YOU
GET TOO CRAZY HERE.
I'VE GOT FULL
RESPECT FOR McKINLEY.
IT'S GONNA BE SOME WHITE
WATER COWBOY [BLEEP] TODAY.
Narrator: TO AVOID THE CENTER
OF THE CREEK'S DEADLY CURRENT,
DUSTIN'S DIVERS WILL
WORK ON THE OUTER LIMITS.
Dustin: RIGHT NOW OUR GOAL IS TO
GET ALL OF THE HARD PACK
WE CAN FIND EXPOSED.
Narrator: THE CREW HAS ALREADY
CLEARED 12 FEET
WORTH OF ROCKS
AND GRAVEL FROM ONE AREA.
BUT NOW THEY'RE
ATTACKING FROM BOTH SIDES
SO THEY CAN REACH
THE COMPACTED MATERIAL
ABOVE THE BEDROCK GOLD.
♪♪
I WANT YOU TO STAY
ON THE RIGHT SIDE
'CAUSE YOU'RE ALL THE WAY
DOWN ON THE HARD PACKED
ON THE LEFT SIDE.
THAT'S ALL YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE TO GO THROUGH
TO GET TO THE GOLD, I THINK.
I BELIEVE THAT.
I REALLY, REALLY BELIEVE THAT.
♪♪
IT'S COLD TODAY.
KEEP THAT MASK
DRY, DRY, DRY, MAN.
DRY, DRY, DRY.
-BE REAL [BLEEP] CAREFUL MAN.
-I WILL.
GOT A LOT OF WATER.
HE'S GONNA BE WORKING WITH
SOME HEAVY, HEAVY WATER TODAY.
BUT IT'S TIME TO REALLY
GET THIS CLEANED OUT.
Man: SEAL IT UP.
Dustin: ALL RIGHT.
OH, YEAH.
Carlos: [ GROANS ]
RIGHT DOWN HERE
HE CAN HANG ONTO ROCKS
AND EVERYTHING ELSE.
LONG AS HE CAN GET
UNDERNEATH THAT CURRENT
HE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE ON THIS
SIDE OF THE BRIDGE,
ABOUT ONE FOOT
AWAY FROM THE WALL.
THAT'S WHERE I WANT YOU TO DIG,
FROM THERE FORWARD.
Rich: [ LAUGHS ]
Dustin: ALL RIGHT.
Carlos: DOWN, DOWN, DOWN.
Dustin: SUPER DANGEROUS.
BOTH DIVERS ARE DOWN
AND IT'S REALLY COMING AT US.
♪♪
Narrator: EXPERT DIVER CARLOS
IS MOVING ROCKS ON ONE SIDE.
Rich: OKAY.
Narrator: GREENHORN RICH IS
DREDGING GRAVEL ON THE OTHER.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
HE SUCKED UP IN HERE.
GONNA BE ONE BIG ROCK
HOLDING EVERYTHING.
THIS [BLEEP]
IS KICKING OUR ASS.
-RIGHT, IT LET GO.
-CAN YOU REACH IT?
I CAN FEEL IT RIGHT HERE.
RIGHT HERE.
Narrator:
RICH CAN'T GET BACK TO DREDGING
UNTIL PAUL AND CASEY
CLEAR THE BLOCKAGE.
THIS THING NEEDS TO BE
ABOUT FIVE FOOT LONGER.
THIS OUGHT TO DO IT.
WE'RE GONNA TRY IT
WITH A DRILL BIT,
A NARROW POINT
AND HOPEFULLY,
THAT'LL HIT THE POINT TO BREAK
THIS THING LOOSE.
SEE HOW THAT WORKS.
♪♪
WELL, HERE WE GO, PAUL.
HERE IT COMES.
HOORAY!
AND WE'RE IN BUSINESS.
PAUL, THANKS, MAN.
GOOD JOB, GOOD JOB, MAN.
YEAH, BUDDY!
Narrator: CARLOS FINDS A ROCK
TOO BIG FOR THE SLED.
Dustin: THERE'S SO MANY ROCKS
WE GOTTA GET OUT
TO GET DOWN TO THAT GOLD.
THE MORE ROCKS WE GET OUT
THE EASIER IT IS TO DREDGE.
WE NEED TO GET MORE OUT.
WE'RE WASTING TIME.
Narrator: PLAN B.
CALL IN THE BIG GUNS.
TIME TO TRY THE GIANT CLAW.
I THINK THAT'S
CARLOS'S FAVORITE TOOL.
HE'S DOWN THERE HOOKING
IT UP RIGHT NOW.
WE'LL SEE HOW WE MAKE OUT.
-HEY!
-[ LAUGHS ]
COME ON, BABY.
LOOKS LIKE THE CLAW CAME LOOSE.
THEY'RE GONNA CHECK
IT AND FIND OUT
WHAT HAPPENED DOWN THERE.
Carlos: OKAY.
Narrator: CARLOS WILL HAVE TO
ENTER THE DANGER ZONE,
THE CENTER CURRENT, TO GET
THE BOULDER INTO THE CLAW.
WE'RE TIRED OF LETTING
MOTHER NATURE WIN.
IT'S TIME TO FIGHT BACK.
♪♪
[ GRUNTS ]
Narrator: DIVER CARLOS MINOR IS
TRAPPED BENEATH HIS DREDGE.
PINNED DOWN BY OVER
A QUARTER MILLION
GALLONS OF WATER POUNDING
DOWN THE CREEK EVERY MINUTE.
OH, MY [BLEEP].
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
WHOO-HOO! YEAH, MAN, I GOT
ROPED IN THAT CLAW, DUDE.
I GOT TANGLED UP IN IT.
YOU JUST STARTED ROLLING IN
THAT SECTION RIGHT THERE.
YOU JUST ROLLED,
YOU ROLLED, YOU ROLLED YOU.
PAUL GOT YOU, MAN.
HE WAS ON TOP OF YOU
LIKE THAT.
YOU CAN'T HARDLY STAND HERE.
IT'S [BLEEP] GOOD LUCK
OUT THERE, DUDE.
YOU SEE ALL THAT,
ALL THAT MESS?
THAT'S WHAT IT'S
LIKE DOWN THERE.
WE'RE CALLING IT.
LET'S JUST CUT IT.
DIVER UP.
DIVER'S COMING UP.
IT KEPT FREAKING
ROLLING ME IN THE CLAW
RIGHT UNDERNEATH
THE FREAKING DREDGE, MAN.
THAT'S ALWAYS ONE OF MY FEARS
IS BEING PINNED DOWN THERE
AND NOT BEING ABLE TO
GET OUT OF THE WATER.
IT'S INSANE UP THERE.
DUSTIN HAS DECIDED TO
CALL IT FOR THE DAY.
I THINK THAT WAS A SMART MOVE.
IT'S RIGHT DANGEROUS [BLEEP].
Dustin: IT JUST GOT A LITTLE
TOO OUT OF HAND.
CARLOS GOT ROLLED.
THAT'S A GOOD TIME FOR US TO
SHUT OFF AND CUT OUT OF HERE.
JUST TRYING TO KEEP
EVERYBODY SAFE.
THAT WATER'S BAD, BAD
MEDICINE RIGHT NOW.
WAY TOO DANGEROUS.
Carlos: BOTH DIVERS ARE ALIVE.
IF MY WIFE WAS RIGHT HERE
AND SHE SEEN THAT
DIVE RIGHT THERE,
SHE WOULD INSISTED
OF ME QUITTING.
GUARANTEE IT.
♪♪
WHOO, HOME SWEET HOME.
THANK YOU FOR THE RIDE.
BEING TRAPPED
UNDERNEATH THE WATER
LIKE THAT IS NO FUN.
HELL, YEAH, I SAW IT.
THERE WAS JUST NO WAY
HE COULD STAND UP.
OKAY, STAND UP.
I'M LIKE I CAN'T STAND UP!
THAT'S GONNA BE THE LAST
TIME THAT HAPPENS.
IT'S JUST SCARY AS HELL.
♪♪
Narrator: THE NEXT DAY...
WE'RE GONNA PUT THE GOLD ON HOLD
UNTIL IT'S SAFE
ENOUGH FOR THE GUYS
NOT TO GET HURT.
Narrator:
DUSTIN HAS A PLAN TO CALM
THE RAGING DIVE SITE.
IT'S STARTING TO GET
A LITTLE TOO DANGEROUS
SO WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO
IS JUST STACK SOME ROCKS
AND HOPEFULLY IT'S GONNA
SLOW DOWN THE WATER
IN FRONT OF IT
AND MAKE THIS BIG POOL
TO WHERE IT'LL BE SAFER.
TODAY THE GOAL IS TO SLOW
THE WATER DOWN A LITTLE BIT
IN THE BACK.
THE ROCKS HAVE TO COME OUT.
WE'LL GET THEM STACKED
RIGHT TO WHERE IT'LL MAKE
KIND OF A POOL BACK THERE.
THE MORE ROCKS YOU GET,
THE DEEPER THE WATER GETS.
SO LESS CURRENT YOU GET.
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE GONNA
BE FOCUSED ON TODAY.
ALL RIGHT?
Narrator: DUSTIN'S PLAN,
TAKE ROCKS FROM THE DIVE SITE
AND DRAG THEM
20 YARDS DOWNSTREAM
TO BUILD A DAM WHICH WILL
RAISE THE WATER LEVEL.
THE DEEPER WATER WILL
CREATE A CALM POOL
FOR THE DIVERS TO
DREDGE FOR GOLD.
♪♪
DUSTIN AND RICH
WILL DIVE FOR ROCKS, NOT GOLD,
UNTIL THE SAFETY DAM IS BUILT.
Rich: SO TODAY DUSTIN WANTS
US TO STACK ROCKS
AND NOT DREDGE.
IT MIGHT BE A RISKY MOVE,
YOU KNOW?
WE HAVE A SHORT SEASON.
WE NEED TO BE DREDGING.
BUT HE THINKS THAT WE CAN
GET THIS WATER TAMED DOWN
AND I JUST DOWN KNOW IF
THIS CREEK CAN BE TAMED.
♪♪
YOU SEE THAT SLED
FULL OF ROCKS?
THAT CAME FROM TWO
OUTSTANDING DIVERS
IN THIS MOST CRAZIEST RIVER
TO GET THAT ACCOMPLISHED.
LOOK AT THAT.
THOSE ARE HUGE FREAKING ROCKS.
Fred: COME ON. ALMOST THERE.
Carlos: [ LAUGHS ]
A VERY REAL BIG ROCK FELL OUT,
SO NOW THE MEDIUM-SIZED
ROCK IS STUCK IN THAT BASKET
AND THEY JUST CANNOT
GET IT OUT OF THERE.
IT'S WEDGED BETWEEN
SIDE TO SIDE.
THEY'RE HAVING A HELL OF A TIME.
[ GRUNTS ]
Fred: UH-OH, FINGERS.
YOU'RE GONNA BREAK THE SHOVEL.
WE NEED THE ROCK BAR.
Carlos:
THEY GOT A CROWBAR AND A SHOVEL
IN THERE AT THE SAME TIME.
Fred: WATCH YOUR FEET WHEN
THAT THING FALLS.
-ALMOST!
-WHOO-HOO!
♪♪
OUTSTANDING, MAN!
DIVER ONE, McKINLEY ZERO.
♪♪
WE'VE BEEN TRYING TO GET THIS
THING BUILT UP BACK HERE.
AS YOU CAN SEE,
THERE'S HARDLY ANY CURRENT.
YOU SEE WHERE WES IS STANDING
THE WATER IS ABOUT
FIVE FEET HIGHER
THAN IT IS BEHIND THESE ROCKS.
IT LOOKS LIKE A BACKYARD POOL.
LIKE A BACKYARD TROPICAL POOL.
♪♪
[ LAUGHING ]
ALL RIGHT, YOU ARE DISCONNECTED
FROM THE UMBILICAL.
THAT WAS AWESOME.
YOU [BLEEP] MADE ME PROUD, DUDE.
Man: GOOD JOB, RICH.
Narrator: RAISING THE WATER
HAS REDUCED THE FLOW
ON THE RIVERBED BY 80%.
♪♪
Dustin: THAT'S AMAZING.
WE'VE MOVED ALL
THESE ROCKS BY HAND.
WE CRUSHED IT.
WE NEVER, EVER
STOPPED MOVING ROCK.
IT WAS PRETTY INCREDIBLE.
THIS IS HOW THIS IS
SUPPOSED TO FEEL.
I FEEL LIKE A LITTLE
JAZZED OFF OF IT.
YOU KNOW, LIKE THIS IS IT.
THIS IS WHY I DO THIS.
I LOVE IT.
IT WAS SO MUCH
RAPID WHITE WATER.
WE COULDN'T WORK IN IT.
AND STACKING ALL THESE ROCKS UP,
IT SLOWS THE WATER DOWN.
I THINK IT'S GOOD.
OUR CURRENT IS JUST
PERFECT RIGHT NOW.
YEAH, LET'S GET OUT OF HERE,
MAN. I'M EXHAUSTED.
I STILL GOTTA HIKE
OUT OF HERE.
-[ BLEEP ]
-YOU'RE RIGHT.
Narrator: UP AHEAD...
Man: [ LAUGHS ]
♪♪
EVERY MINER'S LOOKING
FOR THAT GIANT PAYDAY.
BUCKET OF GOLD.
THAT'S WHAT I'M LOOKING FOR.
MORE GOLD THAN I COULD
EVER SPEND IN MY LIFETIME.
THIS IS MY THING,
THIS IS MY DREAM.
COULD YOU BELIEVE HOW
CALM THIS THING IS NOW?
-LOOKS GOOD TO ME.
-I LOVE IT.
THAT LOOK GOOD TO YOU?
IT LOOKS GOOD TO ME.
HELL, YEAH, I'LL TAKE IT.
Carlos: HEY, REMEMBER HOW THIS
THING ROLLED ME, MAN?
LOOK AT IT NOW, DUDE.
CALM AND SERENE.
IT'S AN OASIS, DUDE.
LOT OF PEOPLE WOULD PAY
FOR SOMETHING LIKE THAT
TO HAVE IN THEIR BACKYARD.
WHOO, CLEAR WATER, MAN.
I SEE THREE FEET.
IT'S GONNA BE A GOOD DAY.
[ ENGINE STARTS ]
Narrator: DUSTIN'S DAM HAS
CREATED A SAFE POOL
FOR THE DIVERS.
THIS IS AS GOOD
AS IT GETS FOR US.
THIS IS PHENOMENAL.
NOW WE CAN GET BACK TO WORK.
Narrator:
PAUL AND CASEY CAN NOW GET BACK
TO DREDGING DOWN TO
THE BEDROCK GOLD.
BASICALLY I'M GONNA
GO DOWN THERE TODAY.
WE'RE GONNA BE DIVING AROUND
11 TO 15 FEET IN SPOTS.
♪♪
Narrator: CASEY IS MOVING
SIX YARDS AN HOUR
WITH FRED'S OLD DREDGE.
PAUL WILL SPEED UP
THE HUNT FOR GOLD
BY DREDGING 12 YARDS AN HOUR
WITH DUSTIN'S HIGH TECH MACHINE.
♪♪
[ BLEEP ]
DUSTIN! DUSTIN!
Narrator:
WES DESIGNED A HEATING SYSTEM
ON DUSTIN'S $17,000 DREDGE.
IF WE CAN'T KEEP THE DIVER
WARM UNDERNEATH THE WATER,
YOU KNOW, THEY JUST CAN'T
STAY IN AND KEEP PERFORMING.
SO IT'S KICKING OUR ASS.
THERE GOES DUSTIN'S
DREDGE AGAIN.
HAVING SOME MAINTENANCE
PROBLEMS AGAIN.
TINK, TINK, TINK, TINK,
TINK, TINK, TINK, TINK, TINK.
NO HOT WATER.
THIS THING IS [BLEEP].
I PROBABLY COULD GO OVER
AND GIVE SOME ADVICE
HOW TO FIX IT
BUT I AM NOT SAYING A WORD.
WE GOT SOMETHING GOING ON
WITH THE HOT WATER UNIT.
IT GOES ICE COLD ON ME.
WITHOUT HOT WATER, 30 MINUTES,
YOU GET HYPOTHERMIA.
ANY TIME THAT DREDGE IS DOWN,
WE'RE NOT LOOKING FOR THE GOLD
WITH THEIR DREDGE.
Narrator: CASEY CONTINUES MINING
WITH FRED'S OLD DREDGE.
HOPEFULLY, THEY'RE
GONNA HAVE THEIR SYSTEM FIXED
READY TO GO.
OPEN UP YOUR HOT WATER
VALVES WIDE OPEN.
LET'S SEE IF WE CAN CONTROL
IT WITH OUR COLD WATER.
I'M USED TO A SINGLE HEATER.
BUT ONCE WE WENT TO TWINS,
IT THREW ANOTHER KINK
INTO THE SITUATION.
Narrator: RICH WANTS TO TOTALLY
REPLUMB WES'S HEATING SYSTEM.
Rich:
THESE NEED TO BE COMBINED.
SO ONE VALVE CONTROLS BOTH.
-I BET $100 BILL.
-I'LL TAKE THAT BET.
YOU TAKE THE TWO OUTPUTS,
YOU GO TO ONE VALVE.
ONE VALVE SLOWS
OR SPEEDS UP THE WATER
AT BOTH HEATERS
AT THE SAME TIME.
YOU CAN PUT THEM
BOTH TOGETHER.
BUT IT DON'T CHANGE THAT [BLEEP]
WHERE IT'S GETTING CLOGGED UP
IT AIN'T GONNA [BLEEP] MATTER.
WE'VE NEVER CHANGED THE FILTERS
AND I THINK THAT'S
THE ROOT OF OUR PROBLEM
IS NOT HAVING
CLEAN ENOUGH WATER.
OKAY.
SOMEBODY'S A LITTLE SENSITIVE
ABOUT THEIR HEATER SYSTEM.
OH, NO.
DON'T GIVE ME ADVICE.
UNSOLICITED ADVICE IS NOT
APPRECIATED AROUND HERE.
NOW YOU KNOW HOW I FEEL.
Rich:
WE'VE GOTTA GET THIS FIXED.
WE'VE GOTTA GET BOTH MACHINES
IN FULL PRODUCTION.
WE'VE GOTTA GET TO THIS GOLD
AND THE CLOCK'S A TICKING.
I DON'T CARE
WHO'S WRONG OR RIGHT.
I JUST WANT IT TO WORK.
I'M STARTING TO LOSE
MY [BLEEP] MIND OVER IT.
I THINK WE'RE
GETTING TOO MUCH SILT
AND IT MAKES IT WHERE
IT'S REALLY HARD
TO GET IT ADJUSTED TO EXACTLY
THE TEMPERATURE THAT THEY WANT.
Dustin: I DON'T ACTUALLY
KNOW HOW THIS WORKS.
WE'RE TAKING
THE WHOLE THING APART.
WES HERE IS FLUSHING
EVERY SYSTEM.
I JUST NEED THIS
STUFF TO WORK, MAN.
GRAVEL IS NOT OUR FRIEND.
Narrator: CLOGGED FILTERS ARE
STOPPING THE FLOW
OF HOT WATER TO THE DIVER.
Carlos: WE'RE HAVING TROUBLE
BECAUSE OF THIS STUFF.
LOOK AT ALL THAT JUNK.
WE'RE NOT RUNNING CLEAN
ENOUGH WATER TO IT
SO IT LET'S THAT [BLEEP]
STOP UP.
Paul: WHEN THIS STOPS UP,
IT KIND OF MAKES OUR
HEATING SYSTEM GO TO HELL.
THAT'S WHERE MY HOT WATER WENT.
WITH THAT FILTER PLUGGED UP,
I DIDN'T GET THE WATER FLOW
I NEEDED TO STAY WARM.
THAT'S THE PROBLEM RIGHT THERE.
THAT WAS IT RIGHT THERE?
YEAH, THAT'S GONNA TAKE
CARE OF IT RIGHT THERE.
LET'S RUN IT AFTER
WE GET THESE BACK TOGETHER.
START IT UP.
LET'S JUST LET IT SHOOT
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
Narrator:
DUSTIN TAKES THE NEXT DIVE
TO SEE IF THE FILTER
CLEANING HAS WORKED.
I THINK WE'RE READY TO
GET DUSTIN IN THE WATER.
♪♪
HOT WATER.
FREAKING NAILED IT, BROTHER.
Dustin:
NOW WE'RE GETTING SOMEWHERE.
Narrator:
CASEY AND DUSTIN CAN GET BACK
TO DREDGING TOWARDS
THE BEDROCK GOLD.
THESE ROCKS PROBABLY WEIGH
MAYBE 1,000 POUNDS.
WHATEVER IT IS,
THE DIVERS CAN'T MOVE THEM.
Narrator:
THE BOULDER STANDING BETWEEN
THEM AND THE GOLD IS
THE BIGGEST THEY'VE FACED YET.
THE SIZE OF A FOUR WHEELER,
BUT 10 TIMES THE WEIGHT.
♪♪
Narrator: A MASSIVE BOULDER
WEIGHING OVER 6,000 POUNDS
IS BLOCKING THEIR
WAY TO BEDROCK GOLD.
FRED CAME UP WITH
THE IDEA THAT WE COULD
EXTEND THE DRILL BIT
AND DRILL FROM THE TOP
SO THEY'RE GONNA HAVE TO COME UP
AND TAKE THE DRILL
BIT AND GUIDE IT
BECAUSE I DON'T HAVE A CLUE
WHERE THE HELL THEY'RE AT.
♪♪
[ DRILL WHIRRING ]
FEELS LIKE IT'S GOING DOWN.
ROCKS ARE SO HARD, THEY'RE
RIGGED UP UNDER THE WATER.
THIS IS GONNA SAVE US
A LOT OF TIME
IF WE CAN GET THESE
ROCKS DRILLED.
WITH FRED MENTIONING
THESE DRILL BITS,
PUTTING THESE BOLTS UNDER WATER,
IT'S REALLY UPPED OUR GAME.
I BROUGHT CASEY A GOODIE BAG
THAT'S GOT SOME BOLTS,
A HAMMER AND A WRENCH
SO HE CAN SET IT IN THERE
AND THEN WE CAN PULL IT.
WE'RE GETTING OUR
BIG WINCH, BIG BLUE.
IF WE'RE USING BIG BLUE
THAT MEANS BIG ROCKS,
BIG ROCKS MEANS BIG DANGER.
[ MACHINE WHIRRING ]
IF THAT ANCHOR BUSTS LOOSE
ON THAT SIDE OR ON THIS SIDE
YOU'VE GOT [BLEEP] STEEL
CABLE COMING TO WHIP SOMEBODY,
CUT SOMEBODY IN HALF
SO WE GOTTA KEEP CLEAR.
[ ROPE WHIRRING ]
Dustin: AAH!
Narrator: CASEY'S DISLODGED ONE
OF THE SURROUNDING ROCKS.
DUSTIN'S HAND GOT
SMASHED PRETTY BAD.
I THINK I MIGHT'VE
BROKE HIS FINGER
SO I FEEL PRETTY BAD RIGHT NOW.
♪♪
IT SMASHED HIS
FINGER PRETTY GOOD,
IT'S A LITTLE BIT SWOLLEN
BUT HE'S TRYING TO TOUGH IT OUT,
HE'S BACK DOWN THERE
HE DOESN'T WANNA COME OUT YET.
Narrator: DUSTIN RETURNS FOR
A FINAL ATTEMPT
TO SHIFT THE MASSIVE BOULDER.
♪♪
Dustin: AAH.
WE'LL SEE HOW WE MAKE
OUT WITH THIS ROCK.
IT'S OBVIOUSLY SOMETHING
BIGGER THAN THEY CAN HANDLE.
♪♪
Dustin: [ LAUGHS ]
Carlos: OH, HO!
-[BLEEP] YEAH, MAN.
I'M GLAD THEY FINALLY
GOT THAT ROCK OUT.
THAT'S ONE ROCK YOU DO NOT
WANT TO HAVE COME DOWN ON YOU
'CAUSE THAT WOULD'VE ENDED
SOMEBODY'S LIFE RIGHT THERE.
THERE'D HAVE BEEN NO SAVING 'EM.
WHAT DO YOU DO FOR A LIVING?
OH, I GO UNDER WHITE
WATER AND I ROLL BOULDERS.
[ LAUGHING ]
I BET YOU ANYTHING THERE'S SOME
GOLD UNDERNEATH THAT.
-YEP.
-I GUARANTEE IT.
[ SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY ]
BIG ROCK BIG GOLD.
Casey: WE KNOW IT'S THERE
SO WE JUST GOTTA GET TO IT
THAT'S ALL THERE IS TO IT.
Narrator: DUSTIN AND CASEY
CAN FINALLY GET BACK
TO DREDGING TOWARDS THE GOLD.
Narrator: REMOVING THE BOULDER
HAS REVEALED A FAULT
IN THE VERTICAL
WALL OF THE CREEK.
IF THIS CRACK CONTINUES
ACROSS THE CREEK BED
ANY NUGGETS FLOWING
DOWNSTREAM WOULD DROP INTO IT,
FORMING A NUGGET TRAP THAT
COULD CONTAIN MILLIONS IN GOLD.
THAT'S GONNA BE
THE ULTIMATE GOLD CATCH.
IT'S PROBABLY NEVER
BEEN TOUCHED THEN,
NOBODY'S EVER GOTTEN INTO IT.
HOPEFULLY THAT GOES ALL
THE WAY ACROSS THE BOTTOM
AND WE'RE GONNA BE SET.
♪♪
THE FORMATION THAT COMES
DOWN THIS WALL RIGHT HERE
IT CREATES A HUGE CRACK.
SO YOU SEE HOW IT'S ALL
BROKEN UP RIGHT THERE?
-YEP.
-IT GOES TO A POINT.
AND IT'S ABOUT TWO TO
THREE INCHES WIDE.
WOW, AN AREA THAT'S KIND OF
JUST FULL OF GOLD.
-CHOCK FULL OF GOLD.
-[ LAUGHS ]
Dustin: I'VE NEVER BEEN
IN THIS SITUATION,
THIS IS THE MOST SIGNIFICANT
DIGGING WE'VE EVER DONE.
THIS IS WHY I DO THIS,
THIS FEELING RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS GOING TO BE THE PAY OFF,
JUST, JUST RIGHT THERE.
♪♪
Carlos: THIS IS A CRAZY JOB
AND I'VE GOT A FAMILY
TO SUPPORT.
I'VE GOT A FAMILY
TO GO HOME TO SO,
IT MAKES ME WANT TO STAY MORE
ALIVE THAN USUAL,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
IT MAKES ME WANT TO FIGHT
FOR MY LIFE.
THE GOLD IS GONNA ENSURE
MY FAMILY IS TAKEN CARE OF.
IF WE FIND GOLD,
THAT'S MY DAUGHTER'S FREAKING
COLLEGE EDUCATION, RIGHT THERE.
NOW UNFORTUNATELY, I DIDN'T
GRADUATE FROM HARVARD.
THIS IS A SKILL
I POSSESSED TO DIVE, YOU KNOW?
THIS IS THE ONLY SKILL
I KNOW WHAT TO DO.
DIVE AND PROVIDE FOR
MY FAMILY, YOU KNOW.
THAT'S WHAT I DO.
♪♪
THIS IS GONNA BE
THE PAY OFF, RIGHT THERE.
IT'S TIME TO DREDGE,
I HAVE TO GET BACK DOWN
AND JUST LINE
MY POCKETS WITH GOLD.
WHAT THEY GOT DOWN THERE
SOUNDS REALLY, REALLY GOOD.
THAT'S GOT EVERYBODY
SO PUMPED UP RIGHT NOW.
Narrator: DUSTIN AND CASEY HAVE
DISCOVERED A CRACK
IN THE CREEK WALL THAT COULD
FORM A PERFECT NUGGET TRAP.
RIGHT NOW THEY ARE TRYING
TO FOLLOW THIS LITTLE WALL,
RIGHT HERE AND THAT MIGHT BE
THE BIGGEST NUGGET CATCH
WE'VE EVER SEEN.
Casey: [ LAUGHS ]
♪♪
I'M ALWAYS LOOKING
FOR GOLD, BROTHER,
FOR THE COLOR, MAN.
THAT WAS AN EXCITING DAY, DUDE.
DEFINITELY HAD A GOOD DIVE.
GOT INTO THAT DEEP
AND IT GOES DOWN INTO
A LITTLE BITTY POINT
AND IF IT'S THAT
WAY TO THE BOTTOM,
AND NO ONE'S BEEN THERE,
WERE GONNA BE RICH.
-[ LAUGHS ]
-THAT'S AWESOME, DUDE.
THIS HAS BEEN
THE MOST EXCITING DAY
I'VE HAD OUT HERE,
BOTTOM LINE.
THE CRACK WHERE THE VAIN IS,
I PUNCHED THROUGH
WITH THE NOZZLE
AND ITS JUST HAULING CHIPS.
THERE SHOULD BE SOMETHING
IN HERE, THERE HAS TO BE.
I ACTUALLY TOOK THE CHANNEL
AND ACTUALLY WENT DOWN IT.
THAT'S WHAT WE'VE BEEN
CHASING SO IT WAS LIKE, "YES!"
WE GOT THIS OPPORTUNITY
NOW TO PULL THAT GOLD OUT.
I HOPE WE DID FIND GOLD BECAUSE,
IT'S AN ABSOLUTE NUGGET TRAP.
IF IT'S NOT THERE,
I WOULD BE REALLY SURPRISED.
THINGS ARE GOING
BETTER THAN I THOUGHT
THEY EVER WOULD.
LET'S DO A CLEAN OUT
AND FIND OUT WHAT'S IN THERE.
I'D REALLY LIKE TO SEE
IF THERE IS ANYTHING IN
THE WALLS IN THIS FORMATION.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S DO A CLEAN OUT.
PAUL JUST DUG
THE FIRST SCOOP IN THERE
AND IT'S VERY PROMISING,
VERY, VERY PROMISING.
-YOU GOT COLOR?
-IT'LL START SHOWING UP.
♪♪
MORE PYRITE Q.
THAT FREAKING PYRITE
PISSES ME OFF.
OH, YEAH! YES, IT IS!
OH, MY [BLEEP].
LOOK AT THOSE NUGGETS, BOYS.
Dustin: THIS IS DANGEROUS
AND YOUR TAKING A CHANCE
BY GOING DOWN THERE.
IF WE WEREN'T
A LITTLE BIT CRAZY,
WE WOULDN'T BE UP HERE.
IT'S THE GOLD.
WHAT'S GOING ON FELLAS?
LOOK AT THE PICKERS
WE GOT OUT SO FAR.
OH, WOW.
IT'S GETTING WAY BIGGER.
THAT'S WHAT WE'VE
BEEN LOOKING FOR.
THIS IS ONE OF THE HARDEST
THINGS I'VE EVER DONE
IN MY LIFE, MY BODY
IS BEAT TO HELL,
BUT I [BLEEP] LOVE
HUNTING FOR GOLD.
-THIS IS A GOOD SIGN RIGHT?
-THAT'S A GOOD SIGN.
YEAH, THAT'S SOME ROUGH
LOOKING STUFF, TOO.
IT HASN'T TRAVELED FAR.
WE JUST CAN'T STOP DOING THIS,
IT'S IN OUR BLOOD.
AND ALL FOR THIS PRETTY
LITTLE YELLOW STUFF, THE GOLD.
WE'VE ALREADY EQUALED UP
WHAT WE GOT LAST SEASON
AND WE'RE ONLY HALFWAY THROUGH.
IT GIVES ME SHIVERS,
I LITERALLY GOT SHIVERS, MAN.
Narrator:
THE TOTALS SO FAR 3 OUNCES
WORTH OVER $3,500
AND THEY HAVEN'T EVEN
REACHED BEDROCK.
THEY JUST HIT A CRACK
IN THE SIDE OF THE WALL,
IF THAT THING CONTINUES
DOWN LIKE THAT,
THAT IS THE BEST MOTHER NATURE
GOLD TRAP THERE EVER WAS.
THIS CRACK MAY HOLD
ALL THE GOLD
THAT I'LL EVER NEED IN IT.
WE COULD ALL WALK
AWAY WEALTHY MEN.
WHOO! THAT'S GONNA BE
A BIG ASS PAYDAY.
THAT'S A VERY BIG POSSIBILITY.
-WE'RE ON THE GOLD BOYS.
-FINALLY STARTING TO PAY OFF.
THIS IS AWESOME,
TODAY IS AN EXCITING DAY.
GOOD DAY, GOOD WEEK.
Narrator: ON THE NEXT
"GOLD RUSH WHITE WATER."
-OH.
-OH!
[ LAUGHTER ]
DIVER UP, DIVER UP.
Carlos: DIVER GOTS NO AIR.
THAT'S AWFULLY QUICK,
AROUND AND BACK DOWN.
WE'RE THAT CLOSE TO THE GOLD.
WE'RE IN BUSINESS, BOYS,
LITTLE NUGGET.
THIS IS OUT OF
MY LEAGUE RIGHT HERE.
WHAT IN THE HELL?
HOLY [BLEEP]?
GET ME THE HELL OUT OF HERE,
MAN, COME ON!
GET ME OUT OF HERE.
JUSTIN?
♪♪