What in the hell?
Look at the water.
Hey, Paul.
Coming up a little bit,
a little bit of sticks, man,
a little bit of debris.
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday, Fred!
75 years old.
You're old.
75 years old,
still diving in Alaska?
That's pretty impressive.
He started to panic down there..
That's how dangerous this is.
We're going to do our first fuel
drop down the mountain.
The crazy that
we do to mine in Alaska.
We're that close to the gold.
We're in business, boys.
A little nugget.
...captions by vitac...
www.vitac.com
captions paid for by
discovery communications
Well, the water is not
perfectly clear this morning, but...
It's nice.
It's not milky.
All right. About a foot,
foot and a half of visibility.
The Dakota boys are 10
weeks into their mining season,
dredging for gold
in one of Alaska's
most remote
and dangerous creeks.
Hey, guys!
Right here.
This is our entire reason
for being here, right here.
So you know how the crack
goes all the way down,
if you were trying
to build a nugget trap,
this is what it would look like.
I just believe it's going to be
chock full of gold,
and now we need to clean it out.
So the hole has to go forward
in order to do this.
Well, I can't wait
to get into this.
Man, this is... it looks like
a good day to dive.
Last week...
...Dustin discovered a crack
in the creek wall...
Yeah!
Yes, it is!
...that gave them
their biggest cleanup yet.
Now we're getting
into gold, baby.
Now Dustin needs his crew
to dredge down through the rocks
and gravel to the pile of gold
at the bottom
of the bedrock crack.
We're throwing the dice.
This is what we're going for.
This is our focus.
All right.
Let's get to work, guys.
So, today, we have to open
the hole up more
so we can get down to the crack.
That promise of the pot of gold
at the end of the rainbow,
I think,
is in every man's heart.
That's what drives you on.
Some men have more of that drive
than others.
Dustin and I have got it.
Dustin has invested
$75,000 in this season.
He needs it to pay off,
or he'll lose it all,
and none of his crew
will get paid.
I'm going to get
the gold out of this hole.
Diving alongside
him is rich Webster.
I'm ready to rock and roll.
Start getting back to digging,
see if we can get down
to some good ole yellow gold.
After 4 hours, Dustin
and rich are 12 feet down,
just 3 feet from bedrock.
Whoa.
Was scary.
I was out of air, dude.
That's the most scariest thing
that's ever happened
to me diving.
Yeah, I bet.
Thank god you were
pulling me, dude,
because I couldn't
get up fast enough.
I was yanking as hard
as I could.
That was good because I
wouldn't have got out in time.
That thing smashed
against my face so hard
when I went to take a breath.
Panicked?
I started to.
I know.
Casey saved my ass.
He saved my ass.
Yeah, that was bad.
Sorry, man.
Glad I got you out.
Thank you. Thank you.
I know.
I owe you one.
You're all right, dude.
That's probably one of
the scariest rescues
we've ever had to do.
He started to panic down there.
That's how dangerous this is.
We got to check
that pop-off valve.
The hose clip
connecting the air lines
to the compressor has blown.
Before anyone can dive again,
Wes switches it out
for a threaded brass coupling.
Yeah.
This is the lifeline
to the diver right now.
We can't afford for this hose
to come off of there like that.
I'm going to give it a shot
and squeeze it down some more.
We'll run it for a little bit
and see if we can get it
to continually run
without popping up.
Luckily, we just happen to have
a tool here to crimp this stuff.
So I think I got that crimped
tight enough
that maybe it will stay
on here this time.
I'm hoping, anyway.
Let's see if that does the trick
right there, a quick fix.
Hopefully, that's going
to take care of it.
So, Fred, is it
back working again?
It's working fine.
The pressure-relief valve
is working perfectly.
Did we double-hose clamp that?
Yes.
I did.
Awesome.
You're the man.
Sorry to ask.
It happened to me in the
Mississippi river at 80 feet.
I made it to within 5 feet of
the surface before the guy says,
"oh, okay.
Here's what the problem is."
One breath,
and there was nothing.
Believe me.
I was coming up.
I think they call them
near-misses.
So I'm going to go back down.
I'm going to get back
in the saddle.
I don't think you should.
You need to get your head
right for this situation.
You had an event today.
I don't think you need to be
back in the water no more today.
Come on out.
You all right, man?
When I heard, "diver up!
Diver up!"
I just turned and started
to come up the wall,
and it was like
That mask went
to my face so hard,
and it's the first time
that I seriously
Started to panic.
It is terrifying.
The best medicine is to get
back in that damn water.
Up next...
Nugget!
That's gold, buddy.
We're getting closer.
The best medicine is to get
back in that damn water.
All right. I'm going.
I'm going.
On his last dive, rich
panicked when his air supply failed.
Now he's bucking his fears,
getting back in the raging creek
and down to the nugget trap.
I'd be lying if I said
I wasn't a little nervous,
but I'm going to go back down.
I'm going to get back in saddle.
I just got to get through today.
Richard, you're clear
to go down.
Dustin heads back
into the creek with rich.
Over thousands of years,
gravity compresses gravel
on the creek bed
into a dense layer
known as hardpack.
This is now all that stands
between them and the gold.
The hardpack is too
tough for the suction hose.
We're coming up.
We got the air chisel.
We have it.
It's ready.
We should stick it down there
today, actually,
but tomorrow we're going
to hit this really hard.
Good job today, fellows.
All right.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Tomorrow, we'll be digging
through hardpack.
I don't think that
that hardpack is more
than 2 or 3 feet deep
at the most.
We're that close to the gold.
They mined in this
area about 100 years ago,
and it takes over 100 years
to make this rock like it is,
so we know that no one
has mined here before.
In order to make this rock
this way, you have
to have thousands of years,
and that's what it took.
A lot of people call this
false bedrock.
Right below this is where
the gold is sitting.
We just got to get through it.
That hardpack has got
that prehistoric cement.
Caveman concrete, brother.
To break through the
hardpack, the crew will use
a pneumatic hammer
powered by an air compressor.
Each strike delivers
150 pounds of pressure
to the hardened steel chisel
3,000 times a minute.
So when he gets down there,
underneath the water,
he's going to essentially
get all this hardpack,
and he's just going
to try to break it up,
pulverize it where he can
suck it into the dredge.
There's a lot of golf
mixed into that hardpack,
and there's a whole lot of gold
underneath the hardpack,
which is what we're after.
Diving with Carlos
today is 74-year-old Fred.
He's going to use
the air chipper.
As he chips, I'll be sucking up
the debris on the bottom,
and we're going to
get after that thing.
Ready?
Let's dive!
We're in business, kids.
Right there.
Yep.
Okay. Here it comes,
brother. Let's do this.
Bright orange hose.
Perfect.
All right.
Let's see how he does.
Wow.
We're getting
desperate for fuel.
I think we need to
check all these fuel barrels.
Oh, my.
We ran out of fuel.
I have no idea
what we're going to do.
Ah!
Oh, Dustin, man.
It was a rookie mistake.
We're in trouble.
We don't have a single barrel
left of fuel,
and I don't know how I missed
this, but I missed it.
I think I'm going through
about a barrel and a half
per week right now,
maybe two barrels.
Between the engines
on each dredge,
generators, and the compressor
for the air hammer, fuel costs
Dustin $1,500 a week.
Without any fuel,
these things don't run.
It's just that simple.
We need fuel,
otherwise everybody
take a big long vacation.
No fuel, no gold.
In the back country,
35 miles north of
Haines, Alaska,
the Dakota boys are shut down.
No fuel means no gold mining.
Getting fuel to where I need
it is really hard.
The helicopters kind of jacked
up their price
a little bit on us,
which I don't have the money
to start throwing at fuel
like I used to.
To avoid a $2,000 heli
lift, Dustin risks a bush resupply.
How about we hook it up
and then run a zipper across it?
We can do that.
What I'm trying to do
is get this 55-gallon drum
400 feet across this ravine
that's about 300-feet deep,
and we don't want to drop it.
Watch your fingers.
That's going to have
to be enough.
All right. If that rope gets
stuck, it will untie itself,
so I didn't think that through.
Come on, baby.
Is that where you want it
right there?
Dustin helied in the ATV
at the start of the season...
But when the dirt
road dead-ends,
there's no way to lower
the 380-pound barrels
safely down the canyon
to the mine site.
Now, we want to
build this long, long pipe
down to another barrel.
Super simple, right?
They've already taken the
barrel over the zip wire from the camp,
along the ATV trail
to the top of the canyon.
Now, they'll connect
4510-foot steel pipes
to get the fuel down the
450-foot drop to McKinley creek
and directly into an
empty barrel at the bottom.
Yeah, I've got to put sealant on
this... these,
before I put them together.
I can't have gas leaking out
of any of it
because it's gonna have
a lot of pressure by the time
it gets to the bottom,
so all these joints have got to
have some kind of compound
on them so they won't leak.
Now the trick is going to be,
"can we put them together
going down the hill?"
Yeah.
We definitely can.
Ready?
Okay.
Right there, it's good.
We decided to go
with the metal pipe
because of the bears
and all the porcupines.
They love to chew up anything
that's plastic,
so the only way to keep them
from poking holes in our pipe,
we had to go with metal.
All right.
Ready to go again.
Standby.
Copy.
Here it comes, Paul.
Copy that.
So far, so good.
We're about a foot
from the edge.
Paul! Can you
send me down a piece?
It's going.
We got this.
We're on a roll.
Talk about relaxing today.
It was a pretty chill day,
though, right?
Come on.
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
Pretty chill.
Hanging from the side
of a mountain.
The crazy
that we do to mine in Alaska.
We got our pipe in.
Well, this is the last
connection that I've got to do,
and we're going to do our first
fuel drop down the mountain.
So like this, now we have
a barrel at the top.
We'll have a barrel down
at the bottom.
All we've got to do
is open our valve,
and it should fill our barrel
down up here with fuel.
Once we have this barrel
with fuel, then we can carry it
back and forth
to the dredge site real easy.
This is going to be
a lifesaver right here.
Dustin, you have a copy?
Yeah, I got you, man.
What's up?
Okay.
I'm ready on my end.
Are you ready to receive
a little bit of fuel?
Yeah.
Give me a little trickle.
Just let me know when you see
a little bit of fuel
out of the bottom.
I am not going to let
very much through to start.
Copy that.
I'll let you know when something
happens, but nothing yet.
You should have a good
flow coming down.
Still nothing, man.
Still nothing.
What are you thinking, man?
I got my valve all the way open,
and there's nothing happening.
I have all of my valves
open, too.
That don't make sense.
Let's try something else
then, huh?
We do have that gas-powered
compressor down there
that will put out 120 pounds
if we can hook a line to it
and just blow this right out.
The compressor will fire a
jet of air down the 450-foot line.
Whatever is in the line,
we're going to push it out.
All right. I'm going
to fire this thing up,
and let's see if we can get
a flow through here.
Okay, I'm going to
send you some air.
I have about 90 pounds of
pressure on the compressor.
Let's see what that will do.
Well, I'll find out shortly.
Okay. Keep
your fingers crossed
that this is going
to come down this time.
I've got everything hooked up,
and I'm going to try
to send you fuel again.
Copy that.
Here we go.
Yeah, got fuel.
I got fuel.
That is amazing.
This will save us
a lot of money.
It's a great afternoon.
We got it cleared,
got fuel going down.
Now we can just concentrate
on getting past the hardpack.
It's all about finding
the gold now.
I like it when a plan
comes together.
Dustin's new system will
save $500 on every barrel of fuel.
Now we can get fuel,
get it up there.
This is so much cheaper,
and we're done with it.
We got it.
And it's got the
Dakota boys back smashing
through hardpack
to the bedrock gold.
We're getting deep finally,
finally.
The crew is just 2 1/2 feet
from bedrock.
We're finally getting our depth
that we need.
Once we get through
that hardpack,
it should be
gold city from there.
Tomorrow should be the day.
We should be able to get
through that hardpack.
Hell, yeah.
It rained like hell last night.
I didn't sleep a wink,
so I've been
thinking about it all night.
So the guys made it down there,
and I wanted to know
what happened.
That rain is something else.
Overnight rainfall
high in the Chilkat mountains
has raised the water level
in McKinley creek by 3 feet.
Getting pretty serious
down there right now,
but mother nature never counted
on guys like Dustin and I.
It could pick up
even more today.
That's what I think
it's going to do
because that big rock
is our marker.
That marker right there always
tells me where we're at.
Another foot high,
the boulders are going to start
rolling into my hole.
As soon as you start hearing
big boulders, I'm out.
That's it.
We're done.
That's how it works.
I mean, you get crushed
at the bottom of this thing.
Right.
Conditions
have gone from dangerous
to potentially lethal down
in the dive hole
Dustin and Casey
are about to enter.
Casey, how about you
don't go down?
I'll go down.
I have so much experience
in this stuff right here.
I just don't want you
to get hurt.
I have the most to gain
or lose from this,
and I'll be down there.
It will be me.
Aw, that would
have been pretty bad.
All right.
Carlos acts
as a lookout upstream.
Looking pretty,
pretty hairy, brother.
Pretty hairy.
His safety zone is about as big
as this right here right now.
That's why I'm looking, man.
I'm looking for any kind of
debris,
like branches, logs, anything.
If you see that, that means
there's been
a landslide up above.
If we start hearing
that McKinley thunder,
what I mean by McKinley thunder,
those rocks roaring down.
You can hear it.
It sounds like thunder.
The rocks hitting each other,
rolling down,
got to come up, man.
Game over on that one.
Well, I'm going to get
some measurements down here.
The guys seem to think they keep
going down all the way.
Let's see how deep
they've actually got this.
14 feet right there.
At 14 feet,
Dustin is just inches away
from where they hit
gold last season.
Oh, my.
Whoa.
Hey, guys.
Hey. Guess what.
What?
We got gold.
Little nugget!
Look at that.
Laying right at the
freaking head of the box.
I'll be damned.
Oh, yeah.
There you go, dude.
That's nice.
Look at that.
It's starting to happen.
We're in business, boys.
Oh, yeah.
We're getting closer.
Hot damn.
I almost want to dance,
but not yet.
Not yet.
Yeah!
That's such a good sign.
It's letting us know that we're
going in the right direction.
That's gold, buddy.
We're getting closer.
When Fred hurt was born,
the United States was at war
with Germany and Japan.
Hey, Fred.
Hey, Fred. Happy birthday!
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday, Fred!
Happy birthday, Fred.
Lord, have mercy.
Happy birthday!
Hello.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Whoo-hoo-hoo.
My old goat.
75 years old.
You're old.
I can handle it.
Probably have to rest a little
bit more than the young ones do.
That's all right.
Holy cow!
It is. Oh!
75 years old, still
diving and hiking in Alaska.
Oh, man.
That's pretty impressive.
If he wasn't working with us,
I'm pretty sure he'd be close
to the grave right now,
but instead, we're keeping
his ass in shape.
Let's see, I think I'll plan
for about another 20, 25 years.
Bad, bad medicine, brother.
Bad, bad medicine, man.
She looks really hairy today.
So the water came up
a whole bunch overnight.
The floods are here.
Have we been talking about it?
It's happening.
I can take this just fine.
It's as muddy
as the Mississippi.
I just hope a bunch of that
Didn't wash back into our hole.
Heavy downpour tonight means
this hole is gone like
we never did anything.
With water levels rising,
Dustin's in a race against time
to get through the hardpack.
He's inches away from a payday
2 years in the making.
It's been raining for a day
and a half, 2 days,
getting pretty serious
down there right now.
Weather like this, I'd
be more worried about a Boulder
rolling down on my head
than anything else
because the water
is already up high.
It comes up anymore,
and it could...
Anything that we have up here...
Right there.
...it could wash it right down
on top of us,
and we're just asking
for trouble if we do that.
All right, guys.
We are so close right now.
I just got to get back
down to it.
The storm,
high in the mountains,
is sending 500 tons of water
crashing down
above Dustin's head
every minute.
Hey, Paul, it's
coming up a little bit,
a little bit of sticks, man,
a little bit of debris.
The water is getting high.
It's getting dirty.
Getting Dustin out in time,
that's what I'm worried about.
I can't believe Dustin
is down in this.
I really can't.
What in the hell?
Look at the water.
My anticipation is that it had
some sort of landslide
came up the side
of the mountain,
probably built up a little bit
of water behind it,
and finally just let loose.
This is the result.
Dustin!
Can you hear me?
I lost comm.
Dustin.
Dustin!
Oh, my.