♪♪
Man: THE WATER'S GETTING HIGH,
GETTING DIRTY!
♪♪
LOOK AT THE WATER!
[ BLEEP ]
STUFF STARTED A LANDSLIDE,
CAME OFF THE SIDE
OF THE MOUNTAIN,
PROBABLY BUILT UP A LITTLE BIT
OF WATER BEHIND IT
AND FINALLY JUST LET LOOSE.
♪♪
OH!
AH.
ALL RIGHT?
CAN'T BELIEVE Y'ALL LET ME STAY
DOWN THERE THAT LONG.
DON'T DO THAT AGAIN!
IT JUST FLIPPED ME LIKE
I WAS JUST A RAG DOLL.
WE'RE DOING SOMETHING
THAT'S WAY TOO DANGEROUS, GUYS.
LET'S GET THE HELL OUT OF HERE,
COME BACK TOMORROW.
♪♪
--Captions by VITAC--
www.vitac.com
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
DISCOVERY COMMUNICATIONS
♪♪
Narrator: THE DAKOTA BOYS ARE
ALMOST THREE MONTHS
INTO THEIR ALASKAN
HUNT FOR GOLD.
OH, [BLEEP].
OH, MY [BLEEP].
THIS IS NOT GOOD.
Narrator:
THEY'VE INVESTED $75,000
BUT ARE NOWHERE NEAR A PAYDAY.
WE HAD A 12-FOOT-DEEP HOLE.
NOW IT'S LESS THAN TWO FEET
DEEP RIGHT THERE.
TWO MONTHS WORTH OF WORK
[BLEEP] GONE DOWN THE DRAIN!
WHAT THE [BLEEP]?
WE DON'T HAVE A HOLE ANYWHERE,
NOWHERE.
YOU SERIOUS, MAN?
YOU'RE NOT PLAYING AROUND?
Narrator: NOW A FLASH FLOOD
AND LANDSLIDE HAVE WIPED OUT
ALL THEIR BACKBREAKING WORK.
JUST LET ME THINK FOR A MINUTE.
ALL RIGHT?
LET'S JUST THINK FOR A SECOND.
THAT'S ALL.
LET'S JUST THINK.
♪♪
YOU START THINKING, "MAN, DO
YOU WANT TO CONTINUE WITH THIS?"
I MEAN, IT'S TOUGH.
ALL THAT HARD WORK
OVERNIGHT IS GONE,
BUT WE'RE RIGHT BACK
TO GROUND ZERO AGAIN,
RIGHT BACK TO WHERE WE STARTED.
I'VE WORKED MONTHS AND MONTHS
AND MONTHS
AND MONTHS AND MONTHS AT THIS
AND ONLY TO HAVE IT
ALL WIPED OUT IN SECONDS.
THERE COULD BE MILLIONS OF
OUNCES RIGHT BELOW US RIGHT NOW,
BUT IS IT GONNA TAKE
A MILLION DIVES TO GET IT?
Carlos:
WHEN DO YOU SAY, "ENOUGH"?
WHEN DO YOU GO BACK
TO YOUR FAMILY AND SAY,
"HEY, I GOT BEATEN UP.
I NEED ANOTHER JOB"?
MY CREW RIGHT NOW IS BROKEN.
I CAN SEE IT ALL IN THEIR EYES.
THEY ALL WANT TO QUIT.
I JUST DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE
I'M GONNA GO FROM HERE.
AH, [BLEEP]!
Narrator:
WINTER IS FAST APPROACHING.
WITH ONLY 3 OUNCES OF GOLD
WORTH LESS THAN $4,000,
THE DAKOTA BOYS
ARE STARING FAILURE IN THE FACE.
♪♪
SO TODAY IT WAS A BUST,
COMPLETE BUST.
IT WAS JUST A PILE OF CRAP.
IT WAS JUST PO...NOTHING.
IT'S JUST HORRIBLE NIGHT.
I JUST DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE
I'M GONNA GO FROM HERE.
IT JUST TOOK ALL THE WIND
OUT OF ME.
I DIDN'T WANT TO BE THERE
ANYMORE,
AND I JUST WANTED
TO WALK OFF AND SAY,
"AW, WE'LL FIND
SOMETHING LATER."
THIS IS A GOLD MINER'S
NIGHTMARE,
AND I DON'T KNOW
WHERE WE'RE GONNA GO FROM HERE.
WE JUST HAVE TO FIND
SOMETHING ELSE.
♪♪
IT'S HEARTBREAKING
WHAT HAPPENED.
IT FILLED IN, BUT WE HAVE
SOME DECISIONS TO MAKE.
WE'VE GOT TO FIND
A BETTER LOCATION.
EVERY YEAR, IT FLOODS,
AND IT COULD FLOOD AGAIN
BEFORE WE EVEN GET BACK
DOWN TO THE HARDPACK.
UNDERNEATH THAT HARDPACK
IS A BUNCH OF GOLD.
DO WE JUST WALK OFF
AND LEAVE THAT?
NOT ON YOUR LIFE.
Narrator: DUSTIN HAS SPENT
HIS LIFE SAVINGS BUYING
ALASKAN CLAIMS
AND MINING EQUIPMENT,
AND SO FAR, NONE OF HIS CREW
HAVE BEEN PAID A CENT.
WE'VE GOT TO STICK
WITH THAT HOLE AND GET IT DONE.
HOW MANY TIMES ARE
WE GONNA DO THIS?
I THINK MOTHER NATURE
IS TELLING US RIGHT NOW,
"LOOK, BOYS, YOU'RE JUST
SPINNING YOUR WHEELS HERE."
I MEAN, IT'S COMING
TO THE RAINY SEASON,
AND WE'RE GONNA BE DONE.
I MEAN, LET'S FIND US
A BETTER PLACE.
WE'VE GOTTEN FLOODED OUT.
WE'VE GOTTEN WIPED OUT,
AND WE GOT OUR ASSES KICKED,
SO LET'S BE SMART ABOUT
WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO HERE
AND UTILIZE
WHAT RESOURCES WE GOT.
WE'RE GONNA GET FLOODED OUT
EVERY YEAR.
I NEED ANOTHER WAY.
WE SHOULD HAVE
AN INSURANCE POLICY.
WE SHOULD GO LOOK
FOR SOMEWHERE ELSE TO DIG.
THERE'S ENOUGH OF US.
WE'LL THINK ABOUT PULLING
ONE DREDGE OUT
AND STARTING SOMEWHERE ELSE
FAST AS WE CAN.
[BLEEP] [BLEEP] TWO OR THREE
DAYS WITH BOTH OF US,
NOT ONE, DIG THE DAMN THING
STRAIGHT DOWN!
IF THERE'S NOTHING THERE,
FINE, LET'S MOVE! [BLEEP].
Dustin: NOBODY CARES ABOUT WHAT
YOU'RE SAYING RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS PART OF THE PROBLEM.
NOBODY WILL LISTEN.
FRED, WE NEED A PLAN B.
WHILE YOU GUYS DIG THIS THING
BACK OUT AGAIN,
I'M GONNA GO SEE IF I CAN FIND
ANOTHER PLACE TO DIG.
I NEED TO SEE SOME GOLD.
WE'RE IN TROUBLE.
♪♪
DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE
I'M GOING RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE GOING STRAIGHT
THROUGH THERE.
Narrator:
DUSTIN AND PAUL SET OFF HIGH
INTO THE CHILKAT MOUNTAINS
TO SCOUT A NEW DIVE SITE
ON CAHOON CREEK.
DUSTIN'S CLAIM IS SO REMOTE,
THE ONLY WAY TO GET THERE
IS ON FOOT.
Dustin: I'VE GOT
A LOT OF CLAIM UP HERE.
DON'T YOU WISH I'D HAVE
BOUGHT EASIER CLAIMS, THOUGH?
NO, NOT REALLY.
THE HARDER THEY ARE TO GET TO,
YOU KNOW THEY HAVEN'T
BEEN TOUCHED.
♪♪
HEY! [ WHISTLES ]
GET THE [BLEEP] OUT OF THERE!
HE'S HUNGRY, MAN.
YEAH.
HE'S LOOKING FOR A WAY DOWN.
GOT TO KEEP OUR EYES OUT
BECAUSE HE'S GOING
TO KEEP TESTING US.
Narrator: THIS CLAIM, A MILE
UPSTREAM FROM THE DIVE SITE,
IS WHERE CAHOON CREEK
FLOWS INTO McKINLEY.
IT'S CLOSER TO THE MOUNTAIN
MOTHER LODE,
THE SOURCE OF ALL THE GOLD.
AT THE START OF THE SEASON...
YEE-HEE!
Narrator: ...FRED AND DUSTIN
FLEW OVER CAHOON CREEK
SEARCHING FOR
THE PERFECT GOLD TRACK.
WHOO! HA HA.
Narrator: NOW THEY NEED TO
LOCATE THE SWEET SPOT
ON THE GROUND.
CAN'T SEE NOTHING FROM HERE,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
WE DEFINITELY NEED EYES UP
IN THE SKY.
Narrator: PAUL GETS OUT
HIS SECRET WEAPON.
Paul:
WE'VE GOT A DRONE OUT HERE.
WE'RE GOING TO TRY TO NAVIGATE
THROUGH ALL THESE CREEKS.
FROM UP HERE,
EVERYTHING IS HIDDEN,
SO WE'RE GONNA GET
THE EYE IN THE SKY.
Dustin: WE'RE JUST ABOVE
CAHOON CREEK RIGHT NOW,
AND WE'RE GONNA FIND
MY NEW DIG SPOT.
HOW [BLEEP] COOL IS THAT?
ALL RIGHT, UPSTREAM FIRST.
-ALL RIGHT.
-YEP.
♪♪
ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
KEEP GOING UP.
THERE'S A WATERFALL
RIGHT THERE.
OH, THAT LOOKS GOOD, MAN.
-THAT'S IT RIGHT THERE.
-OOH, I LIKE THAT.
THAT'S IT RIGHT THERE,
RIGHT THERE, RIGHT THERE.
-THAT'S A WATERFALL --
-THAT'S IT.
-...ON TOP OF A WATERFALL.
-THAT'S WHERE WE NEED TO BE.
THAT DEFINITELY LOOKS GOOD.
LOOK, I'M ALL JITTERY.
[ LAUGHS ]
GOT A WATERFALL,
A NICE WHITE PLUNGE POOL,
GOES DOWN TO A NARROW STREAM.
I MEAN, THAT'S JUST --
IT'S THE PERFECT GOLD CACHE,
DOESN'T GET ANY BETTER
THAN THAT.
Narrator: THE WATERFALL,
PLUNGE POOL, AND NARROW CREEK
PROMISE MONSTER GOLD, BUT FIRST
THEY HAVE TO GET THERE.
THAT'S WHERE I WANT TO GO
LOOK RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE GOING PLUNGE-POOL
HUNTING.
♪♪
Fred: WHOO! THAT'S A HIKE!
Narrator: REFUSING TO GIVE UP,
FRED'S BACK AT McKINLEY CREEK
TO TRY AND DIG OUT
THEIR FILLED-IN HOLE.
♪♪
[BLEEP], MAN.
[BLEEP] DREDGE HOSE IS BURIED!
IT'S ALL UNDERNEATH THAT
[BLEEP].
IT'S BURIED.
NOT A ONE OF US,
NOT ONE OF US THOUGHT
ABOUT BRINGING THOSE HOSES
UP HIGHER IN THE WATER.
YOU GOT TO GET THAT
NOZZLE OUT, MAN.
Fred: WE KNOW THOSE HOSES
ARE REALLY DOWN THERE DEEP.
Narrator: BEFORE THE FLOOD,
THE HOLE WAS
30 FEET WIDE AND 12 FEET DEEP.
THE GRAVEL AND ROCKS CARRIED
BY THE RAGING WATERS
BACKFILLED EVERY INCH OF IT,
BURYING THE SUCTION HOSES
BENEATH 500 CUBIC YARDS
OF WORTHLESS DIRT.
Fred: WE CAN'T JUST LEAVE THEM
HOSES THERE.
I MEAN, THEY'RE STUCK.
WE NEED TO GO AHEAD
AND DIG THEM THINGS BACK OUT.
BOTH DREDGES ARE BASICALLY
OUT OF COMMISSION RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE IN BIG, BIG TROUBLE.
Narrator: WITHOUT THE HOSES,
THEY CAN'T DREDGE OUT THE HOLE.
FRED HAS A PLAN.
THIS IS AN OLD FIVE-INCH.
WE'RE BRINGING THIS ACROSS
TO SEE
IF WE CAN GET
THOSE HOSES OUT OF THERE.
UGH! [BLEEP]!
AWKWARD CROSSING!
LET FRED GET HIS FOOT.
ALL RIGHT. REAL SLOW.
THIS IS SKETCHIER THAN [BLEEP].
-JUST LAY IT DOWN RIGHT THERE!
-OKAY!
-THERE YOU GO.
-AH.
THIS LITTLE HOSE HERE
SHOULD PERMIT US TO RESCUE
THE OTHER TWO HOSES.
Narrator:
THEY'LL DISCONNECT THE BURIED
SIX-INCH HOSE FROM THE DREDGE
AND CONNECT
THE OLD FIVE-INCH HOSE,
BUT IT CAN ONLY MOVE
TWO-THIRDS AS MUCH DIRT.
BUT YOU'RE GONNA SLIDE IT UP
TILL IT HITS RIGHT THERE.
-OKAY.
-ALL RIGHT.
CAN YOU RUN A BIG ROLL
OF TAPE AROUND IT?
I CAN.
JUST TAPE IT
FROM THE OUTSIDE IN.
Carlos: TRY NOT TO KICK
THE [BLEEP] OUT OF IT.
JUST TO HOLD IT ON THERE
IS ALL IT'S FOR.
I GOT YOU.
WE'RE JUST GONNA HAVE TO DO
THE BEST WE CAN WITH IT.
THERE'S ONE OF TWO THINGS
THAT CAN HAPPEN HERE --
WE EITHER GIVE UP, QUIT, OR WE
CAN JUMP BACK IN IT AND HAUL ASS
AND GET BACK TO THE BOTTOM
AND FIND THE GOLD.
WE'RE THERE.
AND THAT'S WHAT NEEDS TO HAPPEN.
[ ENGINE RUNNING ]
-[ LAUGHING ]
-SHE'S WORKING.
WE'RE BACK IN BUSINESS.
♪♪
Narrator: IN THE BACKWOODS,
WAY UP IN
ALASKA'S CHILKAT MOUNTAINS...
-THIS IS DANGEROUS.
-I'M WITH YOU ON THAT ONE.
IT LOOKS A LITTLE BIT SKETCHY,
BUT THIS IS GONNA BE
A GOOD SPOT.
SOMEBODY HAS GOT TO BE
CRAZY ENOUGH TO DO IT.
WHY NOT US?
Narrator: ON A RIDGE,
HIGH ABOVE CAHOON CREEK,
DUSTIN AND PAUL ARE ATTEMPTING
TO REACH A NEW PLUNGE POOL
THEY HOPE WILL SAVE
THEIR SEASON.
IT'S ABOUT 300,
400 FEET DOWN THERE.
-ALL RIGHT.
-ALL RIGHT, DON'T DIE.
LOOKS REAL HARD TO GET TO, MAN.
IT LOOKS TERRIFYING,
SO IT'S PERFECT FOR US.
JUST GOT SUPER DANGEROUS
REALLY QUICKLY.
YOU GOT TO BE PRETTY STUPID
TO DO THIS.
WHOO!
I'M ALWAYS WORRIED I'M A CUT
THAT DAMN ROPE, MAN.
-DON'T CUT THE ROPE.
-WHOO!
WE DO SOME CRAZY THINGS
TO GET TO THE GOLD HERE.
THERE'S NOTHING BUT SLIDE AREA
RIGHT HERE, BY THE WAY,
SO WATCH YOUR STEP!
SO MANY PEOPLE HAVE BEEN HERE
IN THE PAST,
AND ALL THE EASY SPOTS
HAVE BEEN HAD,
SO IT LEAVES US WITH
THESE MOST DIFFICULT SPOTS.
THE HARDER IT IS TO GET
TO THE SPOT,
THE BETTER CHANCE
WE HAVE TO GET THE GOLD.
AH, LET'S SMASH THEM [BLEEP]!
IT'S JUST A PLACE THAT THE OLD
GUYS WOULDN'T HAVE GONE TO
BECAUSE IT TAKES SO MUCH
TO GET TO IT.
WHOO! SHOOTING RAPIDS!
RIGHT THERE IS WHERE
I NEED TO BE.
THESE ARE CLASS-FIVE RAPIDS,
BUDDY.
IF YOU FALL IN IT,
YOU'RE DEAD, MAN.
[BLEEP] BEAUTIFUL.
YOU'VE GOT TO SEE THIS, MAN!
WHOO!
Narrator: THE WATERFALL SWEEPS
GOLD INTO THE PLUNGE POOL
BELOW WHERE IT BECOMES TRAPPED.
♪♪
IT'S COVERED IN A SHALLOW
LAYER OF GRAVEL
SMALL ENOUGH FOR THEM TO DREDGE
OUT IN A MATTER OF DAYS.
♪♪
BUT FLYING IN A DREDGE
AND SETTING UP THE NEW MINE SITE
WILL COST ALMOST $5,000.
♪♪
THAT'S GONNA BE OUR NEXT DIG
SITE DOWN THERE AT THE BOTTOM.
THAT'S WHERE THE GOLD IS AT.
THAT'S WHERE WE'RE GOING NEXT.
♪♪
Narrator: A MILE DOWN
THE MOUNTAIN
ON McKINLEY CREEK...
...FRED AND HIS CREW ARE TRYING
TO RESCUE THEIR BURIED HOSES.
WE'RE JUST GONNA START
WORKING RIGHT DOWN THE HOUSE,
AND WE'RE GONNA KEEP
PULLING IT OUT.
IT'S LIKE STARTING OVER, MAN.
FEEL LIKE I JUST GOT HERE
YESTERDAY.
HEY.
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU, CASEY.
MY NAME'S RICH.
I HOPE WE HAVE A GOOD SEASON.
-ME, TOO.
-NICE TO MEET YOU.
LET'S START OVER.
[ BLEEP ]
WE GOT TO GET THIS HOSE OUT.
SCARY STUFF, AMIGO,
IT'S VERY SCARY STUFF!
EVERYTHING WE HAVE JUST BREAKS,
GONNA GET SOMEBODY KILLED.
-THAT [BLEEP] NIPPLE BROKE OFF.
-IT DID, MUST BE THE SHAKING.
Narrator:
VIBRATIONS SNAP THE COPPER PIPES
SUPPLYING AIR FROM
THE COMPRESSOR TO FRED'S MASK.
IT'S JUST ONE THING
AFTER ANOTHER.
WE FIX THREE THINGS,
AND FOUR THINGS BREAK!
IT'S JUST CONTINUAL.
I DON'T THINK WE'RE GONNA
MAKE ANY PROGRESS
UNLESS WE HAVE TWO DIVERS
ON ONE HOSE.
I FEED [BLEEP] INTO IT.
IT WON'T GO DOWN NO MORE.
♪♪
-HEY, FRED.
-HOW YOU MAKING OUT, MAN?
OH, MAN, I SAW A WATERFALL
WITH THIS HUGE CHUTE ON IT.
I EXPECT IT TO BE
A GIANT DEPOSIT OF GOLD.
HOW'S IT GOING OVER
AT McKINLEY?
BEEN SUCH A DOWN WEEK,
SOME DUMB THING WE DID
JUST LEAVING THEM
HOSES OUT THERE,
AND HOW ABOUT HELPING ME
OUT A LITTLE BIT?
TWO DREDGES WOULD GET IT.
IT'S GOT ALL THAT
KITTY-LITTER STUFF.
EVERY TIME YOU DREDGE IT,
ALL THAT STUFF JUST KEEPS
COMING AND COMING AND COMING
AND COMING AND COMING.
GONNA TAKE FOREVER TO GET
THOSE THINGS OUT OF THERE.
WELL, WE'RE GONNA HELP YOU
OUT FOR JUST A COUPLE OF DAYS.
MAN, I'D REALLY
APPRECIATE THAT.
WELL, YOU KNOW, WE DON'T ALWAYS
SEE EYE TO EYE ON STUFF,
BUT I'LL TELL YOU, I COULD
REALLY USE YOUR HELP OUT THERE.
IT'S ALL SMALL STUFF.
THAT BIG DREDGE,
IT'LL TAKE EVERYTHING OUT.
WE'LL GET TWO DREDGES
BACK ON IT,
AND WE'LL SEE WHAT
WE CAN GET DOWN TO.
♪♪
HEY, BABY.
Fred: DUSTIN IS BRINGING
THE WHOLE ROLL BY HIMSELF.
Narrator: DUSTIN HAS PUT HIS NEW
DIVE SITE ON HOLD
TO HELP FRED DREDGE
OUT THE BURIED HOSES.
Dustin: STILL STUCK?
I'LL GET YOU OUT.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S MAKE [BLEEP] WORK.
WHERE'S MY DUCT TAPE?
Narrator: HE'S BROUGHT ANOTHER
SPARE FIVE-INCH HOSE
THAT THEY MUST NOW CONNECT
TO THEIR SIX-INCH DREDGE.
Dustin: THE WHOLE THING'S GONNA
GET DREDGED DOWN
WITH A FIVE-INCH DREDGE,
AND IF THAT'S WHAT IT TAKES,
THAT'S WHAT IT TAKES.
Narrator: THE FIVE-INCH HOSES
ARE ONE-THIRD LESS POWERFUL
THAN THE HOSES
THEY'RE TRYING TO RECOVER.
I MEAN, THAT'S JUST
WHAT WE HAVE TO DO.
WE HAVE TO GET
OUR HOSES OUT, BRO.
WE HAVE TO GET OUR HOSES.
Narrator: TODAY, CARLOS WILL
DIVE ON DUSTIN'S DREDGE.
HARD, OLD SCHOOL DREDGING,
BROTHER, A DREDGE FEST.
Narrator: AND CASEY WILL BE
FRED'S DIVER IN THE WATER.
THIS ROPE IS TIED TO THE NOZZLE
ON THE SIX-INCH!
ANY QUESTIONS?
GET Y'ALL'S [BLEEP]
ASS IN THE WATER!
TIME TO ROCK AND ROLL.
WHOO-HOO-HOO-WEE!
WE'RE IN.
BY COTTON, MAN,
WE'RE DREDGING ALREADY!
YOU GUYS ARE DREDGING?
WE'RE DREDGING!
THIS IS WHAT WE NEED BACK.
McKINLEY'S TAKEN IT.
WE NEED IT BACK.
Paul: FULL THROTTLE COMING UP.
WOW.
THE LONGER IT TAKES US
TO GET THE HOSES OUT,
THE LONGER IT'S GONNA TAKE US
TO GET BACK TO THE HARDPACK,
AND, YOU KNOW, WE JUST DON'T
HAVE THE LUXURY
OF A LOT OF TIME.
♪♪
Narrator: THE RACE IS ON TO GET
THEIR HOSES OUT.
WE JUST NEED TO WHOOP
THEIR ASS, DUDE.
YEAH.
Carlos: OH, IT'S COMING UP!
COME ON! COME ON! YEAH!
WE GOT IT! WHOO-HOO!
WE GOT IT!
WE GOT IT! WE GOT IT!
[BLEEP] YEAH!
[ LAUGHING ]
-WHOO!
-YEAH!
OH, MY GOODNESS.
Narrator: COMING UP...
-LOOK AT THE GOLD.
-OH, MY [BLEEP] [BLEEP].
-DUDE, THAT WAS JUST HOURS.
-[BLEEP].
Dustin: THIS COULD BE
LIFE-ALTERING GOLD RIGHT HERE.
-THAT'S CRAZY!
-THAT'S GOOD GOLD, GOOD GOLD.
♪♪
Dustin: [ LAUGHING ]
Narrator: DUSTIN AND FRED HURT
ARE RACING TO RETRIEVE
THEIR DREDGE HOSES BURIED
IN McKINLEY CREEK.
Carlos: WHOO-HOO!
IT'S KILLING FRED OVER THERE
THAT WE BEAT HIM. LOVE IT!
YEAH, GRANTED, THEY GOT THEIRS
OUT FIRST, BIG DEAL.
WELL, GONNA GET THIS HOSE
HOOKED BACK UP TO THE DREDGE.
THEY'RE GONNA JUMP OVER
AND HELP US
FINISH UP GETTING OUR HOSE OUT.
THAT'S IT! WHOO!
A LOT GOING ON RIGHT NOW,
SO CRAZY.
♪♪
BOTH THE MACHINES ARE MOVING
JUST A RIDICULOUS
AMOUNT OF DIRT.
IT'S ALL LITTLE, BITTY STUFF,
AND IT'S TONS AND TONS OF IT.
WE JUST KEEP ON PUSHING.
Narrator: DUSTIN'S SIX-INCH
DREDGE IS WORKING ALONGSIDE
CASEY'S FIVE-INCH TO
DIG OUT FRED'S HOSE.
[BLEEP].
BUT THAT'S WHAT THE PROBLEM IS.
KEEP DREDGING OUT THERE!
DAMN IT!
GET UP ON THE SIDE
OF THE [BLEEP] HOSE!
-ROGER THAT.
-ON THE BACK SIDE OF THE HOSE.
FRED IS SO UPSET THAT WE'RE
COMING OVER TO HELP HIM,
AND HE JUST CAN'T
STAND IT, SORE LOSER.
[ LAUGHS ]
Fred:
IT KIND OF PISSES ME OFF.
I MEAN, IT JUST --
IT'S FRUSTRATING.
Narrator:
FRED USES A RATCHET WINCH
TO TRY AND SPEED UP
THE HOSE RESCUE.
LOOK WHAT YOU'RE DOING
TO THAT HOSE.
YOU'RE GOING TO RIP THAT HOSE
IN HALF TO PROVE A POINT.
THE WHAT?
YOU'RE GOING TO RIP THAT HOSE
IN HALF TO PROVE A POINT.
-[BLEEP].
-HE'S GONNA BREAK IT.
HE IS SO MAD THAT WE BEAT HIM.
I CAN SEE IT JUST LOOKING,
SO MAD!
HEY, LOOSEN UP ON
THAT THING BEFORE YOU
[BLEEP] THAT THING UP!
EVERYBODY HAS LOST
THEIR [BLEEP] MIND,
STARTING TO HAVE A CATASTROPHE
CLUSTER SCREW HERE.
YOU'RE DESTROYING THE HOSE!
I WISH EVERYBODY
WOULD JUST CALM DOWN.
IT'D GO FASTER
IF WE'D JUST CALM DOWN.
-YEAH! YEAH!
-WAY TO GO, CARLOS!
-YEAH!
-WHOO-HOO!
Fred: VERY HAPPY WE GOT BOTH
OF THE HOSES OUT OF THERE.
HOW WE GOT THEM OUT OF THERE WAS
AGGRAVATING TO SAY THE LEAST.
♪♪
HEY, FRED, BIG OLD SPLIT,
LOOK AT THAT.
WHAT THE [BLEEP]?
GOT A BIG SPLIT IN OUR HOSE.
THAT'S NO GOOD.
IS THAT WHERE
THE COME-ALONG WAS?
GOOD JOB, FRED.
SNAPPED OFF THE [BLEEP] HOSE.
YOU DID GREAT, MAN.
WAY TO BE IMPATIENT.
FINALLY GOT OUR HOSE OUT.
WE'LL MAKE SOME REPAIRS.
IT TOOK A LITTLE BIT OF DAMAGE,
AND WE'RE GONNA GET BACK
TO KICKING ASS,
GET THIS HOLE CLEANED OUT.
WELL, IT HAPPENED A LOT
FASTER THAN WE THOUGHT.
I THOUGHT WE HAD THREE DAYS TO
GET THESE DAMN HOSES OUT,
AND THESE GUYS DID IT
IN 1 1/2 DAYS.
WE GOT THEM OUT!
Narrator: BEFORE THE FLOOD,
THEIR HOLE WAS 12 FEET DEEP,
3 FEET FROM BEDROCK.
THAT IS 9 FEET.
YEAH, DUDE.
WE'RE ALMOST BACK.
-CARLOS!
-YEAH?
9 FEET [BLEEP]!
9 FEET! [ LAUGHS ]
WE KNOW THERE'S GOLD DOWN THERE,
SO LET'S JUST KEEP GOING.
I HAVE ENOUGH TIME TO FIX THIS.
-WHAT ABOUT CAHOON?
-CAHOON CAN WAIT.
WE'RE GONNA PUT IT ON HOLD.
WE NEED TO FIND OUT
WHERE THIS GOES.
WE HAVE TO FIND THE BOTTOM.
Narrator:
THE SPEED OF THE RESCUE MISSION
HAS CHANGED DUSTIN'S MIND.
HE'S STAYING PUT.
CAHOON'S PLUNGE POOL
IS OFFICIALLY ON HOLD.
WE'RE GETTING TOWARDS THE GOLD.
THE BLOOD PRESSURE GOES UP.
THE EXCITEMENT LEVEL
IS GOING UP.
Narrator: PROFESSIONAL DIVER
CARLOS AND ARIZONA
GOLD-MINE OWNER CASEY
LEAD THE CHARGE TO BEDROCK GOLD.
Dustin:
IF WE MAKE THIS LAST PUSH,
WE CAN GET DOWN TO THE BOTTOM.
IT'S TIME TO FIND
SOME GOLD AGAIN.
HERE WE GO AGAIN.
ALL RIGHT?
I'M GONNA GET THE GOLD
OUT OF THIS HOLE.
THIS ISN'T OVER WITH.
Narrator: WITH BOTH DREDGES
RUNNING FULL TILT
AND WITH NO BOULDERS TO MOVE...
...THE DAKOTA BOYS ARE BACK
IN THE GAME,
JUST 6 FEET FROM BEDROCK GOLD.
WHOO-HOO!
YEAH!
WE'RE BACK IN BUSINESS.
ANOTHER DAY, I THINK,
AND WE'RE GONNA HAVE ALL THIS
[BLEEP] OUT OF HERE,
WHATEVER IT TAKES!
♪♪
ALL YOU GOT TO DO
IS JUST KEEP DIGGING, MAN.
[ BLEEP ]
COPY THAT.
DAMN IT!
ALL THIS [BLEEP]. [ GROANS ]
Narrator: CASEY'S HOSE HAS
BECOME COMPLETELY JAMMED UP
WITH THE FINE MATERIAL
WASHED IN BY THE FLOOD.
THAT'S [BLEEP] HEAVY.
-FULL OF [BLEEP].
-YEAH, THAT'S [BLEEP] PACKED.
-[ GROANS ]
-GOOD JOB, MAN!
HE MUST HAVE JUST JAMMED IT
IN THE [BLEEP] DIRT.
HAVE TO FLIP IT UPSIDE DOWN.
START AT THE BOTTOM.
YOU GOT TO HIT IT.
HE JAMMED IT IN THE DIRT
ON PURPOSE.
HE DIDN'T WANT TO GO DOWN.
IT'S EMPTY.
HEY! DON'T DO THAT AGAIN!
YOU TOOK TOO MUCH.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
Narrator: DUSTIN BELIEVES CASEY
JAMMED THE HOSE
DELIBERATELY TO GET
A BREAK FROM DREDGING.
I DON'T THINK HE WANTS
TO BE DOWN HERE PERIOD.
I KNOW.
THAT'S WHY HE DID IT.
-YEAH, HE DID IT ON PURPOSE.
-FILLED UP ON IT.
I KNOW HE [BLEEP]
DID IT ON PURPOSE.
[ GROANS ] [ BLEEP ]
THAT BOY JUST MADE ME SO MAD.
IS THIS WHAT I HAVE
TO DEAL WITH NOW?
♪♪
THAT [BLEEP] HEAVY.
FULL OF [BLEEP].
Narrator:
CASEY'S HOSE IS BLOCKED,
AND DREDGING IS HALTED.
Dustin: "OH, I MESSED UP.
I GUESS I CAN'T [BLEEP]
DREDGE ANYMORE."
GET THE [BLEEP] OUT!
GET OUT!
[BLEEP] DONE TODAY! GET UP!
YO, NEXT TIME, IF YOU WANT
TO COME OUT OF THE WATER
AND DON'T WANT
TO GO BACK DOWN, SAY,
"HEY, DUSTIN, I DON'T WANT
TO GO BACK IN THE WATER."
ALL RIGHT?
IT'S THAT EASY.
I HAVE NO PROBLEM WITH THAT.
-ALL RIGHT?
-I GOT IT.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO WORK
WITH HIM.
THAT BOY JUST DID THAT
ON PURPOSE,
SO WE PULLED HIM OUT
OF THE [BLEEP] WATER.
[BLEEP]. THAT'S SOME
[BLEEP] RIGHT THERE.
WE DON'T NEED ANYBODY
THAT DON'T WANT TO WORK.
THAT'S JUST NOT ONE OF US.
THAT'S NO HELP AT ALL.
CASEY'S TIRED. I GET IT.
WE'RE ALL TIRED, BUT HE DECIDED
HE DIDN'T NEED TO BE
IN THAT WATER ANYMORE,
AND INSTEAD OF JUST BEING A MAN
AND SAYING, "HEY,
I'M TOO TIRED TO DO THIS"...
[ GROANS ] [ BLEEP ]
I CAN'T STAND THAT [BLEEP].
BE A MAN!
THESE GUYS ALL WANT TO,
LIKE, FREAK OUT.
I'VE BEEN DOWN THERE ALL DAY,
BUT DUSTIN WANTS TO GET MAD.
I DON'T REALLY GIVE A [BLEEP].
HE'S SABOTAGING THE DIVE
SO HE CAN GET OUT,
KNOWINGLY JAMMED
THE SIX-INCH DREDGE
INTO THE DIRT
AND LET IT CLOG UP.
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYBODY ON MY
JOB EVER DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT,
AND I JUST ABOUT LOST MY MIND.
THESE GUYS ARE ALL AMAZING,
AREN'T THEY?
ALL THEY DO IS WANT TO SIT HERE
AND [BLEEP]
YELL AT EACH OTHER,
AND THEY NOT FINDING [BLEEP]
FOR GOLD, AND IT'S, LIKE,
EVERYONE'S FAULT BUT THEIRS.
THEY'RE NOT SEEING
THE BIG RESULTS IN THE BOX.
THEY BETTER START THINKING
ABOUT OPTION TWO.
YOU CAN'T STEP UP, GET THE HELL
OUT OF HERE, BUT DON'T PUT YOUR
[BLEEP] ON ME.
WE GOT A REAL PROBLEM.
YOU KNEW EXACTLY
HOW TO CLOG THAT
[BLEEP] THING UP, AND YOU DID.
-NOT INTENTIONALLY.
YOU [BLEEP] SABOTAGED
THAT [BLEEP],
AND I HAD TO WORK MY [BLEEP]
ASS OFF FOR IT.
NO WAY.
I WOULD NEVER DO THAT.
I WOULD NEVER SABOTAGE A LINE,
NEVER.
TELLING YOU,
I'M HERE TO HELP YOU.
I'M NOT HERE
TO DO THAT [BLEEP].
I'VE BEEN WORKING
ALL DAY AT IT.
IT JUST...[ SIGHS ]
I'M A LITTLE
WORKED UP RIGHT NOW.
I'M TRYING TO CALM MYSELF DOWN.
I GOT [BLEEP] FURIOUS, DUDE.
YEAH, I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU
GET MAD AT ME BEFORE.
YOUR WHOLE ATTITUDE
THROUGH THE WHOLE THING,
I'D LIKE TO BELIEVE YOU.
-OKAY.
LET'S JUST STOP
AT THAT AND SAY...
I'D HAVE TO BE INSANE TO DO
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
...LET'S NEVER LET THIS
HAPPEN AGAIN.
-OKAY.
-AND LET'S MOVE ON FROM THAT.
BUT IF YOU WANT TO BE
OUT HERE, BE OUT HERE.
YEAH.
BUT IF YOU DON'T WANT TO BE
OUT HERE, JUST GO, DUDE.
ALL RIGHT.
THAT [BLEEP]
CAN'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
DON'T EVER [BLEEP]
DO THAT AGAIN.
ALL RIGHT.
♪♪
WHO DOES THAT? LIKE, REALLY?
I'VE ONLY BEEN HERE FOR MONTHS
AND MONTHS AND MONTHS WORKING.
LIKE I WOULD ACTUALLY SABOTAGE
A JOB AND THEN,
AFTER YOU WORK THAT HARD,
BE TOLD, "YOU WANT TO BE HERE?"
OKAY.
I'VE HEARD IT ALL NOW.
[ LAUGHS ]
Narrator:
WITH THE HOSE UNBLOCKED,
THE DAKOTA BOYS ARE GOING
FULL STEAM AHEAD FOR GOLD.
IT'S DETERMINATION.
THAT'S ALL THAT'S
GONNA HOLD US IN.
ALL I KNOW, MAN, WINTER
IS JUST AROUND THE CORNER.
WE HAVE TO DO THIS NOW.
WE HAVE TO GET IT DONE NOW.
♪♪
Narrator:
RICH DIVES IN CASEY'S PLACE.
THIS SAME DREDGE IS GONNA
CLOG UP AGAIN.
THIS THING IS NOT PULLING.
RIGHT NOW, RICH CAN BARELY RUN
ANY MATERIAL IN IT.
DUSTIN'S HEARING IT FROM RICH.
THERE'S NO POWER.
MAYBE HE'S BITING
HIS OWN TONGUE.
MAYBE HE'LL SAY SORRY TO ME.
I DON'T THINK DUSTIN
WILL EVER APOLOGIZE.
HE DOESN'T GIVE A RAT'S ASS.
PROBABLY FROM THAT RIP THAT FRED
DID WHEN HE TRIED
TO CRANK OUT THE HOSE.
I CAN'T EVEN LIFT
THE [BLEEP] THING!
IT'S CLOGGED UP RIGHT HERE
BECAUSE IT'S NOT TAKING
THE WATER OUT OF THE HOSE.
IT FEELS REAL HEAVY.
HELPING FRED GET HIS
SIX-INCH HOSE OUT,
HE HAD IT TIED ON
WITH THE COME-ALONG,
AND IT ACTUALLY RIPPED
THE HOSE IN TWO,
SO WHEN HE TAPED IT UP,
ALL IT DOES IS IT CATCHES ROCKS.
Narrator: THE HOSE ON FRED'S
DREDGE HAS A FOUR-INCH TEAR,
SUCKING IN WATER AND CAUSING
A LOSS OF POWER AT THE NOZZLE.
THE SUCTION ISN'T STRONG ENOUGH
TO MOVE MATERIAL UP
TO THE DREDGE,
SO THE HOSE
KEEPS GETTING BLOCKED.
I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO EVEN
REALLY RUN THIS MACHINE.
IT SHOULD EAT QUADRUPLE
THE AMOUNT OF ROCKS
THAT IT'S DOING RIGHT NOW.
IT'S REAL POSSIBLE THAT CASEY
MAYBE GOT A BUM RAP.
♪♪
EVERYBODY, WE'RE GOING
TO LOSE CASEY HERE.
HE'S GONNA GO TO MEDICAL.
Narrator: CASEY IS TAKEN DOWN
FOR TREATMENT
TO THE MEDICAL CENTER
30 MILES AWAY.
WHAT HAPPENED WITH CASEY
WAS A MISINTERPRETATION
ON MY SIDE OF THE SITUATION.
I THOUGHT THAT HE SABOTAGED
HIS DIVE.
TURNS OUT THAT FRED
KINKED THE HOSE SO BAD
THAT IT WON'T WORK.
IT WAS NOT CASEY'S FAULT,
AND I HAD NO RIGHT
TO DO WHAT I DID,
AND I'M GONNA TELL HIM SO.
♪♪
AS YOU KNOW, THIS IS
OUR WEDDING ANNIVERSARY,
AND WHAT I'VE DONE IS,
I BROUGHT THE LIGHT FAMILY BAND
UP HERE
AS MY ANNIVERSARY GIFT TO YOU.
[ WOMAN SINGS INDISTINCTLY ]
♪ EVERY MOON RISE THE SEA
♪ AND I CAN'T ESCAPE
♪ AND SO WE DON'T WANT TO
♪ MY ONLY...
[ SINGS INDISTINCTLY ] ♪
♪ OH
-THANK YOU.
♪♪
Narrator: HIGH IN ALASKA'S
CHILKAT MOUNTAINS,
THE DAKOTA BOYS ARE A MAN DOWN
AND STRUGGLING AGAINST THE ODDS
TO REACH A FORTUNE IN GOLD.
FRED'S SUCTION HOSE
IS BADLY DAMAGED.
TO GET DOWN TO THE GOLD,
THEY NEED TO FIX IT.
OUR ONLY OPTION RIGHT NOW
IS TO JUST SHORTEN IT
AND DEAL WITH IT.
♪♪
WE'RE THE CREW
THAT DON'T GIVE UP.
WE'RE KIND OF LIKE A HOUND DOG
ON THE TRAIL.
PRETTY SOON, WE'RE GONNA
HIT IT BIG.
[ LAUGHS ]
Narrator:
THE DAKOTA BOYS HAVE SUCKED OUT
ALL THE MATERIAL WASHED IN
BY THE FLOOD IN JUST TWO DAYS
BECAUSE THERE WERE
NO BOULDERS TO MOVE.
-HELL, YEAH.
-ALL RIGHT, GUYS!
WE'RE BACK AT HARDPACK!
ALL RIGHT!
WE'RE BACK TO WORK AGAIN!
-YEAH!
-WHOO-HOO-HOO!
Narrator:
NOW ONLY THE HARDPACK STANDS
BETWEEN THEM AND BEDROCK GOLD.
-YEAH!
YEAH, MAN.
BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
WE'RE BACK
IN THE [BLEEP] GAME NOW.
WE HAVE AN EXCELLENT, EXCELLENT
CHANCE OF GETTING THE GOLD NOW.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
AN EXCELLENT CHANCE.
♪♪
IT'S TIME TO GET BACK DOWN
TO THIS GOLD, MAN.
I'M BACK DOWN TO HARDPACK.
DIDN'T TAKE NEAR AS LONG AS
I THOUGHT IT WOULD.
WE GOT THIS.
GONNA FIND OUT WHAT'S ON
THE BOTTOM OF THIS DAY THREE.
♪♪
HEY, MAN.
-HOW ARE YOU?
-BEAT.
YOU AND I GOT TO HAVE
A TALK, MAN.
SHOOT.
I OWE YOU AN APOLOGY.
OKAY.
I ACCUSED YOU OF SOMETHING
YOU DIDN'T DO, THE HOSE THING.
IT WAS MESSED UP,
AND IT WASN'T YOUR FAULT.
I WAS JUST FLAT-OUT WRONG.
-I NEVER SEEN YOU ACT LIKE THAT.
-YEAH.
I MISREAD THE SITUATION.
I DO HAVE A BAD TEMPER,
BUT I FELT LIKE I WAS JUSTIFIED,
AND I WASN'T, SO SORRY
I MISJUDGED YOU LIKE THAT.
-OKAY.
-YEAH.
-WELL, THANK YOU.
-THANK YOU, MAN.
I'M GOING TO TRY TO TELL YOU
SOME OTHER NEWS.
I WENT DOWN, SAW A DOCTOR.
I'VE GOT INTESTINES PUSHING
THROUGH REALLY HARD,
POKED THROUGH MY ABDOMEN
AND THROUGH MY UMBILICAL,
AND THEY WANT TO GO
HAVE SURGERY ON IT.
-[ BLEEP ]
-THAT'S SERIOUS, DUDE.
I DON'T WANT IT TO BECOME
LIFE-THREATENING.
I WANT TO TAKE CARE OF IT NOW
BEFORE IT DOES.
Carlos: YOU'RE HURT, MAN.
GO HOME. GO RECOVER.
SO I'M BROKE NOW, BUT I...
THIS IS A HARD JOURNEY.
-YEAH.
-APPRECIATE THE WORK, MAN.
-OH, IT'S BEEN A HARD JOURNEY.
-YEAH, MAN.
-OH, MAN.
-THIS IS THE HARDEST THING.
THIS IS THE HARDEST THING
YOU EVER DO, MAN.
IT IS. THIS WHOLE THING
MAKES ME FEEL LIKE [BLEEP].
GO HOME WITH YOUR FAMILY, MAN.
RECOVER FOR YOUR FAMILY, MAN.
I MEAN, THAT'S ALL YOU
CAN DO, MAN.
-RIGHT.
-THAT'S ALL YOU CAN DO.
-THAT'LL BE THAT.
-GOOD LUCK.
YOU'RE PICKING UP HIS SLACK.
-DAMN IT, CASEY, AGAIN!
-I GOT YOU AGAIN.
-GOT ME AGAIN!
-[ LAUGHS ]
ON YOUR SICK BED,
YOU GOT ME AGAIN.
YEAH, ON MY SICK BED, YEAH.
WHO THE HELL ARE WE GONNA
BLAME STUFF ON NOW?
-DAMN IT!
-YOU'RE RIGHT.
DAMN IT, CASEY!
-HANG IN THERE.
-IT WAS A TRIP.
-I'M GOING TO MISS YOU, BRO.
-SORRY, MAN.
♪♪
HAVING TO WORK IN ALASKA,
BROTHER,
IT'S GONNA TAKE
SOMETHING OF YOU, MAN.
THIS ADVENTURE, THIS MISSION,
THIS FEVER,
YOU'RE GOING TO SACRIFICE
SOMETHING, MAN.
CASEY WILL BE WITH US
IN SPIRIT, BRO.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I HOPE THESE GUYS
CAN FIND GOLD SOON.
WINTER IS COMING, SO I WISH THEM
THE BEST OF LUCK.
THAT'S IT.
♪♪
-DOESN'T THAT LOOK LIKE [BLEEP]?
-RICH, THAT'S ALL GOLD.
Rich: THERE'S GOLD, ISN'T IT?
Narrator: COMING UP ON
"GOLD RUSH: WHITE WATER"...
-WHOO!
-OH, MY [BLEEP]!
-THAT'S NUGGETS, BOYS!
-[ LAUGHS ]
Narrator: ...WILL THEY FINALLY
STRIKE IT RICH?
LOOK AT THOSE NUGGETS, DUDE!
SHUT THE [BLEEP]!
-LOOK AT THAT!
-LOOK AT THAT [BLEEP]!
OH!