You get to a point
with your parents...
...where all you can do with them
is eat. You can't talk anymore...
...but you wanna at least try
and keep your mouths moving.
And they're so anxious for it,
you know. You come in:
"How was the plane?
You must be hungry.
How did you sleep?
Ready for breakfast?"
My mother will argue with me
about what I like.
"Can I have a piece of pumpkin pie?"
"You don't like pumpkin pie."
"Yes, I do."
"Since when?"
"What's the difference?
Can I have it?"
"No. I have never seen you eat
a piece of pumpkin pie."
Mr. Peterman sent me over here
for a physical...
...because as you may
or may not know...
...he and I are going on a trip
to Kenya.
Africa.
It's my first such mission
for the company.
The Masai Bushmen
wear these great sandals...
...and we're gonna knock them off.
Not the Masai, the sandals.
- I'll need a urine sample.
- Right.
Africa? Do you know how hot
it gets there?
Like 150 degrees.
Your skin is gonna be
simmering with boils.
Oh, come on.
You coming to The Tonight Show?
Yeah, yeah. My parents wanna
come too, is that okay?
- Sure. My parents will be there.
- The Tonight Show?
Yeah, they're in town.
You wanna go?
- Are you doing new material?
- No.
I don't think so.
Hey, the super's in my bathroom
changing my showerhead.
- Have they changed yours?
- No, he's doing mine next.
- They're low-flow, you know.
- Low-flow?
Well, I don't like the sound of that.
So, what are your parents
doing here in New York?
Well, they were humiliated.
After the impeachment,
my father left office in disgrace.
- So, what are their plans?
- Well, this is the problem.
They're moving into this new
development. Here's the pamphlet.
"Del Boca Vista."But they're
not quite ready to go back...
...so they're in seclusion here
for a while at Uncle Leo's.
The three of them
in that tiny apartment?
No, Leo's not there.
He's got a girlfriend, Lydia.
- In fact, he moved in with her.
- Uncle Leo's having regular sex?
Yeah, I know, it devalues
the whole thing.
- Hello.
- What time do we have to be...
...at The Tonight Show on Thursday?
- You gotta be there at 4:30.
- But it comes on at 11:30.
Yeah, well, they tape it in the
afternoon and then they air it at 11:30.
- How long they been doing this?
- Thirty years.
Helen, did you know that they
tape this thing in the afternoon?
All right. I'll see you later.
Georgie, how come your parents
never moved to Florida?
Yeah, that is odd, isn't it?
- Yeah, it is.
- I mean, they're retired.
There's no economic reason
for them to be here.
They have no friends.
No social reason for them
to be here.
- You're all grown-up.
- Yeah, they're through ruining my life.
What the hell
are they still doing here?
Let me see this pamphlet.
All right, I'll...
I'll get back to you.
- Hello?
- Where can I buy some ice?
Your father likes a lot of ice.
I don't know.
Maybe get an ice tray?
- I can do that.
- You know, Dad just called me.
Yeah, I know.
His phlebitis is acting up.
Yeah. All right.
Well, I got some people here.
- Okay.
- All right, bye.
- You see this?
- What?
Any thought pops into their head,
they call me...
...because it's a local call now.
I'm used to a 1200-mile buffer zone.
I can't handle this. Plus, I got
the dinners, I got the pop-ins.
- They pop in. It's brutal.
- Any idea when they're going back?
The only way out is if
Leo breaks up with his girlfriend...
...and moves back in. Then they
would have to go back to Florida.
How's that gonna happen?
It's about time you called your uncle.
We gotta do this once a week.
Once a week?
So how's Lydia?
She's a real tiger.
I don't know how you do it.
- What?
- Well, a man like you...
...limiting yourself to one woman.
I don't know. It's none of my business.
What are you talking about?
- Well-
- Look at this.
I told them medium rare.
It's medium.
- It happens.
- I bet that cook is an anti-Semite.
He has no idea who you are.
They don't just overcook
a hamburger, Jerry.
Fine. Anyway, the point
I was making...
...before Goebbels
made your hamburger here is this:
A man like you could be
dating women 20 years younger.
Come on, Uncle Leo,
I've seen the way women look at you.
When's the last time you looked
in the mirror? You're an Adonis.
You've got beautiful features,
lovely skin.
You're in the prime of your life here.
You should be swinging.
If I were you,
I'd tell this Lydia character:
"It's been real."
Move back into that bachelor pad
and put out a sign:
"Open for business."
Believe me, I thought about it...
...but she is so perfect in every way,
I can't see a flaw.
Well, keep looking.
Oh, hi, Mr. Peterman.
Do you realize how short
the Kalahari Bushmen are?
I'm gonna look like a giant
to those guys.
I'm afraid I have
some bad news, Elaine.
It appears you will not be
accompanying me to Africa.
What? Why not?
I'm afraid it's your urine, Elaine.
You've tested positive for opium.
- Opium?
- That's right, Elaine.
White Lotus. Yam-yam.
Shanghai Sally.
Well, that's impossible.
I've never done a drug in my life.
Dr. Strugatz must have
made a mistake.
Not a chance.
I'm afraid I'll just have to find someone
else to accompany me on my journey.
The Dark Continent
is no place for an addict, Elaine.
Obviously, Mr. Peterman,
there's something wrong with this test.
I don't take opium.
Let me take another one, please?
I'll call the doctor right now.
I'll take a pop urine test.
- All right, Elaine.
- Oh, thank you, Mr. Peterman.
I'll be ready in three minutes.
Boy, it's cold outside, huh?
Oh, these New York winters.
Bitter cold. Bitter.
I was out for five minutes before.
I couldn't feel my extremities.
What extremities?
You know what the temperature
in Florida is today?
Seventy-nine.
That's almost 80.
Yeah, I read someplace,
the life expectancy in Florida...
...is 81. And in Queens, 73.
So, George, why are you here?
What, I can't stop by
and visit my parents?
What's this?
That's where the Seinfelds
are moving. They got a great deal.
- Yeah?
- You know what they got in Florida?
Jai alai.
You bet on the games,
you clean up.
- I don't bet.
- Well, what about the dolphins?
You can swim
with the dolphins there.
I don't swim.
Well, you could pet them.
They come right out of the water
onto the sidewalks.
Are you trying to get rid of us?
I care about your comfort.
Be it here in Queens...
...or 1200 miles away.
No?
Jerry. Jerry!
- You too, huh?
- Yeah.
These showers are horrible.
There's no pressure.
- I can't get the shampoo out.
- Me either.
If I don't have a good shower, I am not
myself. I feel weak and ineffectual.
- I'm not Kramer.
- You? What about me?
I got The Tonight Show tonight.
I'm gonna have to shower
in the dressing room.
- Where you going?
- Well, I gotta find another shower.
- They got you too?
- This is awful.
I'm not Newman.
"Rid"? Ma, come on.
The word is "care.""Care."
- Oh, Elaine. Yeah.
- Kramer, you look terrible.
Yeah. I need the keys to your
apartment. I gotta take a shower.
- What's wrong with your shower?
- There's no water pressure.
- Why didn't you go see Jerry?
- Jerry's got nothing.
Newman's got nothing. You're
the one who's got the good stuff.
And I need it bad, baby, because I feel
like I got bugs crawling up my skin.
- Now, you gotta help me out.
- Not on my watch!
I won't have you turning my office
into a den of iniquity!
- What's wrong with you?
- Get your fix somewhere else!
Go on, beat it!
- Mr. Peterman, what are you doing?
- Elaine, you're out of control.
You need help.
I know what you're going through.
I, too, once fell under the spell
of opium.
It was 1979.
I was traveling the Yangtze...
...in search
of a Mongolian horsehair vest.
Oh, for God's sake.
I had got to the market after sundown.
All of the clothing traders had gone.
But a different sort of trader
still lurked.
Mr. Peterman, I don't know
what's going on here.
I am not addicted to anything.
Oh, Elaine.
The toll road of denial
is a long and dangerous one.
The price? Your soul.
Oh, and by the way, you have
till 5:00 to clear out your desk.
You're fired.
- All they serve is chicken?
- There's more food down the hall.
Here, wrap it up. We'll take it home.
- Oh, hey.
- Oh, hi.
Hello, Seinfelds.
- Hello.
- Hi, Estelle.
This is your dressing room?
They treat you like Toscanini.
Oh, Jerry, I don't know
how you can do this.
I'm so nervous for you.
Actually, I'm drunk.
Hey. Hey, how is Florida, huh?
We just bought a new place
down there.
I know. We were looking
at the brochure.
"Just a taste,"he said.
That was all it took.
- You what?
- Why, you thinking of moving?
- Not really.
- Because if you are, you shouldn't.
There's nothing available there.
Are you telling me there's not one
condo available in Del Boca Vista?
That's right.
They went like hotcakes.
- How'd you get yours?
- Got lucky.
Are you trying to keep us out
of Del Boca Vista?
I know this doesn't seem
like work to you...
...but if you'd conduct the psychopath
convention down the hall...
...so I could just get
a little personal space.
How could I have
tested positive twice?
Once, I can understand.
That's a mistake. But twice?
Yeah, it's hard to figure.
I mean, I've lost my job.
I can't go to Africa.
I was gonna meet
the Bushmen of the Kalahari.
- The Bushmen?
- And the Bushwomen.
Excuse me.
I couldn't help overhearing.
I notice you're eating
a poppy seed muffin there.
Yeah, I eat these muffins
all the time.
Well, you know what opium
is made from.
Poppies!
Welcome back.
Talking with Jerry Seinfeld.
Jerry, let me ask you,
I saw some people back there...
- ... they look lik e family. Is that family?
- I got some family backstage.
My family's nuts. They're crazy.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
My Uncle Leo,
I had lunch with him the other day.
He's one of these guys
that anything goes wrong...
...he blames anti-Semitism.
Know what I mean? The spaghetti's
not al dente? Cook, anti-Semite.
- Right there, yeah.
- Loses a bet on a horse?
- Secretariat, anti-Semitic.
- Even the horse- Even the animal.
The High Holy Days in the temple?
Rabbi, anti-Semite.
Listen to this. My Uncle Leo broke up
with his girlfriend because of my bit.
She thought it was funny, so he
accused her of being an anti-Semite.
They had a fight, now he's
moving back to his apartment.
Know what this means? My parents
are gonna go back to Florida.
What?
What number is this?
Oh, I'm terribly sorry.
Kramer, my parents are gonna have to
move back to Florida. Isn't that great?
Yeah, well, I'm really happy for you.
Hey, you're not giving it to me, man.
What's wrong?
I just took a bath, Jerry. A bath.
- No good?
- It's disgusting.
I'm sitting there in a tepid pool
of my own filth.
All kinds of microscopic parasites
and organisms...
...having sex all around me.
Well, you used to sit
in that hot tub.
Jerry, that was super-heated water.
Nothing could live in that.
- Chicken?
- Oh, yeah.
Well, this you're not gonna believe.
I found out why
I was testing positive for opium.
- Poppy seeds.
- Yep, that makes sense.
- Yeah.
- Here you want some chicken?
- Yeah, thanks.
So I'm gonna get tested again later.
Hopefully I'll get my job back,
and I will be on my way to Africa.
Hello, Newman.
Hello, Jerry. Well, I may have
a solution to our little problem.
- Elaine, will you excuse us?
- Oh, come on, Newman.
I have a private matter to discuss
with my fellow tenants.
If you don't mind...
- Jerry-
- Look, sister, go get yourself...
...a cup of coffee, all right? Beat it.
All right. Now, here's the lowdown.
Through a certain connection...
...I've been able to locate
some black-market showerheads.
They're all made
in the former Yugoslavia.
And from what I hear, the Serbs
are fanatic about their showers.
Not from the footage I've seen.
Nevertheless,
sometime this afternoon...
...behind the market diner,
an unmarked van will be waiting.
I'm expecting the call at any time.
- Are you in?
- I'm down.
Jerry?
So, Georgie,
we have some big news for you.
- Big news?
- We're moving to Florida.
What?
You're moving to Florida?
That's wonderful. I'm so happy!
For you! I'm so happy for you!
Oh, what do you need
this cold weather for?
Has nothing to do with weather.
- It's because of the Seinfelds.
- What do you mean?
They don't want us there,
so we're going.
We're moving right into
Del Boca Vista!
- So you're moving there for spite.
- Absolutely.
No one tells Frank Costanza
what to do!
That's right! Who the hell are they?
How dare they?
So, Georgie, are you gonna
come to visit us?
Oh, every chance I get.
Jerry, Jerry!
I'm busting, I'm busting!
- Well, what's going on?
- My parents are moving to Florida!
- Are you kidding?
- Can you believe it? It's happening!
It's finally happening, I'm free!
- Well, where are they moving to?
- Del Boca Vista.
That's where my parents
are gonna live.
- I know.
- We can visit together.
Every five years!
- That's incredible.
- You know why they're moving there?
- Why?
- To spite your parents.
- To spite my parents?
- Yeah.
- Your parents are crazy.
- I know, they're out of their mind.
- I don't believe it.
- Fantastic.
- My parents are moving back too.
- Beautiful!
I'm sorry Leo's moving back here.
I'm not ready to go back to Florida.
He was getting along so well
with that woman. What happened?
Hello?
- This is Frank Costanza.
- What do you want?
You think you can k eep us
out of Florida?
We're moving in
lock, stock and barrel.
We're gonna be in the pool.
We're gonna be in the clubhouse.
We're gonna be all over
that shuffleboard court...
...and I dare you to keep me out!
I'm sorry, we can't go back
to Florida.
I can't believe
I didn't push for this sooner.
You have no idea how your life
is gonna improve as a result of this.
Food tastes better.
The air seems fresher.
You'll have more energy...
...and self-confidence
than you ever dreamed of.
- Hello.
- Hello, Jerry, it's your father.
- Oh, hi, Dad.
- Is it all right...
...if we move in with you
for a little while?
- What was that?
- Nothing. A bottle broke, that's all.
What do you mean,
you're gonna move in here?
Because the Costanzas
are moving in to Del Boca Vista.
- But it's a big complex.
- You don't understand.
You gotta have a buffer zone.
All right, fine. Come over here.
What?
They're not going back to Florida.
- They're moving here.
- What? Why?
Because your parents
are going down there.
My buffer zone just went from
1200 miles down to two feet.
You gotta do something.
Hey, I'm sorry. You had
your buffer zone for many years.
It's my time to live, baby.
You know what you're doing,
don't you?
You're killing independent Jerry.
I gotta go see my Uncle Leo.
I think he may have made
a big mistake.
- Move back with Lydia?
- Come on.
You're lucky to have anybody.
Last week you told me I was
in my prime. I should be swinging.
Swinging?
What, are you out of your mind?
Look at you. You're disgusting.
You're bald. You're paunchy.
All kinds of sounds are emanating
from your body 24 hours a day.
If there's a woman that can take your
presence for more than 10 seconds...
...you should hang on to her
like grim death.
Which is not far off, by the way.
- But she's an anti-Semite.
- Can you blame her?
You don't think he minds
us staying here, do you?
Why would he mind?
We're his parents.
- Hi, Elaine.
- Hello.
- Jerry's not here?
- No.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
A poppy seed.
It must have been in the chicken.
Oh, I'm dead.
I'm going to the doctor's
in a half an hour.
- Why?
- It's a long story.
Just a second.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Wait. What are you gonna do
in there?
What am I gonna do
in the bathroom?
You gotta do me a favour.
- Elaine, I really have-
- Hold on a second, Mrs. Seinfeld.
I need your sample.
You want my urine?
I need a clean urine sample
from a woman.
- I don't know.
- Oh, please, Mrs. Seinfeld, please?
Well, what am I gonna do it in?
- Well, one of those glasses.
- Jerry's glasses?
Oh, yeah. He won't mind.
Come on, you're his mom.
I could- Should I use a coffee cup?
- Yeah, coffee cup's fine.
- Or maybe I could use a juice glass.
Yes, yes. Fine, fine.
A juice glass. It's perfect.
- This one is kind of scratched.
- It doesn't matter.
- All right. How-? A milk glass.
- A milk glass, a juice glass.
- Any glass, just pick a glass.
- Jerry really doesn't...
- ... wash these very well.
- Mrs. Seinfeld, choose a glass.
Pick a glass, Mrs. Seinfeld.
All right. I got everything here.
I got the Cyclone F series...
...Hydra Jet Flow, Stockholm
Superstream, you name it.
What do you recommend?
- What are you looking for?
- Power, man, power.
Like Silkwood.
- That's for radiation.
- That's right.
Now, what is this?
That's the Commando 450.
I don't sell that one.
No, that's what we want,
the Commando 450.
No, believe me. That's only used
in the circus for elephants.
- Just give it to us.
- We'll pay anything.
- Give me the money.
- We've got the...
- What about Jerry?
- He couldn't handle that.
He's delicate.
It's nice being back at Leo's.
Jerry's place was too small.
First Leo breaks up,
then he goes back.
What the hell's going on?
- Who is it?
- It's the super.
We're installing new low-flow
showerheads in all the bathrooms.
Low-flow?
I don't like the sound of that.
So as a result of your test
being free of opium...
- ... I am reinstating you.
- Oh, yes!
What a load off.
So when are we going to Africa?
I'm afraid I can't take you.
What? Why not?
Elaine, according to your
urine analysis, you're menopausal.
You have the metabolism
of a 68-year-old woman.
But I wanted to see the Bushmen.
Oh, and one more thing.
You may have osteoporosis.
- Well, it's been a great visit.
- Jerry, I'll tell you.
First thing I'm gonna do when
I get back to Florida is take a shower.
At least the Costanzas
changed their mind about moving.
- They couldn't bear leaving George.
- George must be happy about that.
You have no idea.
Take my swim trunks.
I won't need them.
What does he want
with your swim trunks?
Why should they go to waste?
Oh, yeah.