(Lauren)
'Oh, my gosh, this is 75% off.'
That's cute.
And so, who's all coming
for New Year's?
Are your friends from Laguna?
I'm inviting my friends Jill,
Natania, and Lo.
So you've known Lo
since high school?
I've known Lo since,
like, third grade.
You'll really like Lo.
She's hilarious.
Is she anything like Jen?
'No, I-I told you, like,
one of the reasons'
we were, like,
got in a big fight
and, like, didn't talk
over the last
couple years is 'cause of Jen.
So, we'll just get ready
at your house?
'Yeah, we'll all meet
at our house.'
I have a feeling that Heidi
will end up spending
most of the night with Spencer,
which is understandable.
- It's New Year's.
- Oh, yeah, it's her boyfriend.
But I mean, that's why I went
and invited other people
was 'cause I didn't wanna depend
on her to be, like--
Mm-hmm, to be, like,
the third wheel or something.
'Are they coming in the limo?'
Spencer's not allowed
in the car.
- No? I know. I know.
- No.
I'm so happy.
This New Year's is gonna be fun.
'I know. I just hope
it's better than last year.'
Mm-hmm.
♪ Whao-o-o ♪
♪ Won't you bring light
to my day? ♪
♪ Won't you be somebody new ♪
♪ It'll be good ♪
♪ It'll be like coming home ♪
♪ And tell me
that you wanna be... ♪♪
Out of the park, Whitney.
Out of the park.
Go, Whitney, go!
- 'Yeah!'
- Whoo! Go!
Run!
'Yay, Whitney!'
Whoo! Go, Whitney!
- Go, team.
- Whoo!
- Yay!
- Hi, girls.
Whoo-hoo!
- You did fabulous.
- Thanks for coming.
So do you, do you guys always,
like, switch around positions?
Usually I play, like, either
catcher or in the outfield.
So, what do you guys think
you're gonna do for New Year's?
I guess, you know what
when I asked Heidi something
about New Year's, she's like,
"What are you gonna do for
New Year's?"
and I was kind of, like...
What are we gonna do?
Well, she's gonna
wanna be with Spencer
on New Year's, but...
I kissed, like, three guys
on New Year's last year.
It was like, the most,
the sluttiest moment of my life.
I'm just gonna grab
someone next to me.
I did that two years ago.
I remember you telling me
about that.
We're gonna have a good
New Year's this year.
♪ Oh when I walk
out into the sun ♪
♪ Walk out into the sun oh ♪
♪ Sounds like everyone... ♪♪
(Spencer)
'It'd be fun shopping for a
New Year's eve dress, isn't it?'
(Heidi)
Really? Have you ever shopped
for a New Year's eve dress?
I do have two sisters,
sweetheart.
So, yes, actually.
So, what's the plan
for New Year's, huh?
Do we get our own night,
or what?
- We'll go to dinner together.
- Without the posse?
Yes, without the posse, and then
we will all go to Area
together afterwards.
- Who's "We all?"
- I made up with them.
With Lauren and her friends
from Laguna.
I'm done hanging out
with Lauren.
I'm really excited to spend
New Year's with Lauren, though.
Like, 2006 was a hard year
on our friendship
and I think that this year's
gonna be a lot better
and I wanna make more
of an effort, and I wanna spend
New Year's with her too,
and I want to spend it
with my two favorite people.
She means a lot to me too
and it's just unfair to me.
- I think I--
- That was serious.
I know. I know. Give me a hug.
I don't want anything
to be unfair to Heidi.
I'm a very fair person.
So, I got some big news
I wanna talk to you about.
What's the news?
- The news is...
- What?
What if I was moving out
of the condo
and I was gonna get a house...
...with Princess Heidi?
No? Maybe?
I mean...
I mean, obviously, I would
love to move in with you.
But?
I mean, I made a commitment
to live with her.
You know, I'm trying
to work things out.
I feel like that would
just make it worse in a way.
That gets really annoying.
And it's really...
I don't wanna say affecting
our relationship
but it definitely
doesn't help it.
Well, at least put that
in your head because I think
it's a good solution
because, uh--
It's not like we won't
have to worry about it anymore.
It's, like,
she'll always be my best friend.
Like you guys
are still best friends?
She spends
all her time with Audrina.
Think about it, dear.
'So, just think about it.'
♪ You say you say ♪
♪ Someday someday ♪
♪ You'll be changed ♪
♪ Some way some way... ♪♪
We're gonna be at Area
for the countdown, right?
We're planning, I don't know,
like, what your deal is
but we're planning on going
there and, uh, Area's countdown.
We have to leave earlier,
'cause we have to pick up a guy
that I met last night
that I'm bringing with us.
- You met a guy last night?
- Yeah.
If you had come out,
you would know that.
But he's visiting from Colorado,
so he's only out here
for like,
another five days, I think.
I asked him out, I called him
and I'm picking him up.
When you see him, you'll be like
"That's not Lauren's type."
Maybe that's a good thing.
Um, it's a very good thing.
Have you met my type?
Audrina!
[laughs]
- Audrina, you look pretty.
- Thank you.
What's your New Year's
resolution?
Audrina and I
are gonna take kickboxing.
- Yeah.
- Chh.
(Lauren)
'Huh, Audrina?'
It's, like, such a good workout.
- 'I want to try it.'
- 'Hey, Lauren.'
Should we just
grab something to eat?
We can order, like, a pizza.
Pizza and champagne.
[chuckles]
Are you guys gonna
do it up or down?
(Heidi)
'We like it down.'
Oh, my God! Twins, Audrina.
Alright. I got to go to dinner.
And, uh, but we'll all meet up
later tonight at Area?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
[rock music]
Here you go, man.
Look at the princess,
looking so beautiful.
Get this door open
for the princess.
I don't even
wanna go to the club.
I just want to take
you home right now.
I wish we could just go home.
Why can't we? Oh, that's right.
'Cause you have another
boyfriend, named
Lauren Conrad, that we have
to meet at the club.
Have you given
any thought to my offer?
Honestly,
in the next couple of years
I wanna move in with you.
It's like, I love you.
I wanna be with you.
I just feel like...
It's not like I'm sitting here
demanding anything from you.
I feel like if I move out...
...it was gonna compromise
our friendship.
It shouldn't be this,
like, juggling act.
It's like, there's a big
difference between friends
and people you're romantically
and intimately involved with.
I'm trying really hard,
and I'm trying hard to keep you
happy, and I'm trying hard
to keep her happy
and I know it shouldn't be
a balance like that
because it's like,
you are who I'm in love with.
I don't understand,
why can't Lauren live with...
...somebody else, like Audrina?
[instrumental music]
♪ I love the starlights... ♪
[laughs]
Look at that...
- Okay. Smile again.
- My face.
♪ ...I'd dream tonight ♪
- Can you stand?
- No.
Alright, guys. Ready? Smile.
One, two, three.
- Cheers.
- 'Cheers to New Year's.'
To spending New Year's with
people most important to us.
- 'Happy New Year.'
- Happy New Year's.
- Cheers.
- Guys, I'm excited for tonight.
I've never had
a New Year's kiss.
I think everyone should have
I have had a New Year's kiss
for the last four years
but I've only had one good one.
Lauren, where's Heidi?
Why isn't she here?
'Heidi's at dinner
with Spencer, and she's--'
- Is that, like, her man?
- That's her boyfriend.
- I love Heidi. She's so sweet.
- 'I love Heidi, too.'
- 'I heard Spencer was an ass.'
- What did you hear?
You guys will have to get
your own--
(Lauren)
'I'm not saying anything.
You'll meet him.'
You tell us what you think
later, like, after you meet him.
- 'Hey, are we ready to go?'
- Okay, let's go.
♪ We're gonna rock
this world it's ♪
♪ A party planet
gonna make it shake ♪
♪ Right off it's axis
gonna rock this world ♪
♪ It's a party planet ♪
♪ They're gonna hear us
all across the... ♪♪
- Are we waiting for Heidi?
- No. Let's go.
- Hello.
- Hi.
(Spencer)
Let's not go to club.
I could care less
about any person in Area.
(Heidi)
Spencer, please don't
make this hard.
- I actually have a speedboat.
- Really?
So during the summer,
every day we have off
me and my roommates, we go out.
It's just a blast, so...
It's really hard, because...
Especially for me.
I'm, like, a pretty big guy.
And it's hard to get me up
out of the water.
You're tall? Are you?
I thought so.
[chuckles]
[cheering]
Oh, my God. These are intense.
Whoo!
- Hi! Happy New Year's!
- How are you?
- Happy New Year's to you too.
- Happy New Year, boss.
- Good to see you.
- Good to see you too, guys.
- My love.
- Do you know my boyfriend?
- Spencer.
- Spencer...
Hi, Rob.
- 'My New Year scarf.'
- I know.
That was embarrassing.
Okay.
[indistinct chattering]
- Hi, guys!
- Hi-i-i!
Yeah.
Very nice.
- Cocker spaniel!
- Oh!
I really want
a cocker spaniel...
[laughs]
[instrumental music]
(Lo)
'Oh, my God!'
[all cheering]
We're gonna be like...
Oh, my God. Olson's down there.
Whoo!
[all cheering]
[indistinct shouting]
[cheering]
(all)
Three! Two! One!
Whoo!
Happy New Year's!
Happy New Year!
[yells]
Happy New Year's!
[indistinct chattering]
Wait, that's not our car.
Valet!
Hey, in 2007, I had...
Happy New Year!
No, in 2007.
- Go handle your business.
- Go handle.
- Go handle it.
- But you gotta handle.
(Spencer)
Don't play games.
You like how they just leave you
and don't even say goodbye?
Great friends, right?
Your best friends.
Was there a goodbye, Heidi?
I didn't see a goodbye, Heidi.
- Baby.
- Oh-ho.
Oh, reality check for you.
Who am I? I'm Lauren.
Walk right by Heidi
without saying goodbye.
I'm just saying
that's the reality.
- It's a reality check.
- Please, stop. Please.
- I love you. I don't...
- I love you. Stop.
I don't stop.
[instrumental music]
(Elodie)
'Here's a bunch of invites'
'that we had for another party'
and we need to use
the envelopes again.
(Heidi)
'Um, how was your New Year's?'
Oh, it was okay. I worked.
What did you do?
Um, I was kind of disappointed
because I, like, made an offer
to, like, I wanted to be
with Lauren all night
because obviously
Spencer didn't want to spend
New Year's with like,
me and my friends
and then Lauren was mostly
with Audrina all night.
Like, I hardly saw her,
and I'm like
"I came here to be with you,
not just
for you to be with Audrina--"
Well, they probably
didn't even want Spencer there.
And...
...Spencer asked me
to move in with him.
No way.
[laughs]
He was just like, "You know
"every day, I love you more
"and I just
never thought I'd feel
"this way about somebody,"
and...
- "I didn't know what love was."
- Really?
And I've never been
in love like this.
Like, this is a different level.
I didn't even know what to say
'cause it's like,
obviously I really
want to live with him,
but it's like...
- You know--
- Are you ready for that?
Like, you are really
so young still.
Exactly. It's like, am I ready?
Did you mention that to Lauren?
Um...not yet.
What are you thinking right now?
[instrumental music]
- It's nice out today.
- I know.
- How was your New Year's?
- I had a date.
- You had a date?
- I was, like, determined.
I was like, "I need to have
a New Year's kiss."
'That's important.'
And he was just here on vacation
which is part
of his appeal
'cause, like, he'll go away.
He's gone now. So nothing.
No, I think he's still here,
but..
But it could have been, like,
a nice little winter fling.
It was. I kissed him on
New Year's. That was my fling.
Like, the crowd there
was kind of random.
- It was? Who came up?
- Mm-hmm.
My friend Lo came up,
who was, like
my best friend in high school.
- That's so fun.
- 'It was really fun.'
It's good to be with old friends
on nights like that.
This year, I just wanted,
like, be with people...
You know what I mean? Just like
a good group of friends.
And you got to be with Heidi
on New Year's.
We met Heidi and Spencer
at Area.
I only really got to see her for
like, two minutes on New Year's.
- Shut up.
- Better than nothing.
They've been together
for a long time now, huh?
- Mm-hmm.
- 'Like, how many months?'
I don't know. I expected them
to screw it up by now.
I-I-I didn't think it was
gonna last as long, either.
Nobody did.
'I was so happy to spend
New Year's with, like'
four or five of my closest
friends and those are all
people that really
have been there for me.
- 'Yeah.'
- You know what I mean?
I'm very sad
you weren't there, though.
I know.
I mean, yeah, we're all trying
to find out, like
who our true friends are
and stuff, and it sucks, but...
[instrumental music]
[laughs]
- Hi. How are you?
- How are you?
- I'm good. Thanks.
- It's under "Spencer," for two.
- Here's your Virgin Lemon Drop.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you, sir.
- No problem.
This one's mine. That's yours.
Cheers. I love you.
Cheers. I love you more.
- I do. I really do.
- No, you really don't.
Heidi, I deal with all your
crazy friends, all your drama.
And I deal with all that...
for you.
Heidi's the one
with all the baggage.
You know what?
I don't have baggage.
You have...
I have a lot of people
in my life.
- Lot of things that I'm doing.
- 'I call them baggage.'
You call them baggage,
but that's a lot of things
that I have to deal with.
There's a lot of people
in my life. It's...
Really, go cry to yourself,
because I don't need--
♪ Do-do-do ♪♪
I've been thinking a lot,
and I think it's really rude
that you've chosen
Lauren over me.
I think it's really rude
that you'd make me choose.
- Oh, is that what you think?
- Yeah.
Yeah, you are choosing
to live with somebody
that abandons you
out in front of clubs.
I don't think so.
Well, I don't really know why
she did that, but there
has to come a time when she
has to let go a little bit.
I was never, like,
"I dislike Jason" or anything.
It's like, she was gonna move,
she moved in with him
in the summer,
and I never was like
"We're gonna stop
being friends."
That never happened.
So I'd expect the same courtesy.
- Whoa. This is a new statement.
- Yeah.
So who are you gonna
get a house from?
You don't worry about that.
All you worry about is how
you're gonna break it to Lauren.
[instrumental music]
(Lauren)
'You are wearing flats.'
Well, I came straight from work.
I know.
Thanks, Brittany.
Thank you so much.
- Oh, thank you.
- 'Sure.'
- Ginger. I love ginger.
- You're gonna love this.
I believe you.
It's heated up on the top.
[coughs]
- Sorry.
- You okay?
I just had ginger juice
go up my nose.
[both laugh]
Lo, just go like this.
No, it's, like, up here
in the back of my head.
Oh. Does it burn your brain?
Yeah, it really does.
It's burning my brain.
I didn't realize that ginger
was that potent.
- You okay now?
- Yeah. Yay.
So, did you have a good
New Year's overall?
Yeah. It's so fun being back
in LA, like, with everybody.
Do you know, someone told me
that Jen was gonna go
to Area on New Year's?
I did hear
that she was going to go.
She had, like,
bought a ticket and everything.
She's probably, like
"Ah, I have no more friendships
to destroy."
'Who does she hang out with?'
I'm guessing
that she is spending
time with her friends at USC.
I don't know,
it's disappointing to me that...
Like, that friendship
had to end in the way it did.
Honestly, like, at this point
I would so much rather
have, like, a few good friends
than a lot of fake friends.
I know, and especially being
in LA, it's really hard to find
people here that are sincere.
- Do you know what I mean?
- Someone who is real.
Um, who is moving into
your apartment when Heidi
moves out with Spencer?
Did she tell you that?
Heidi came up to me
on New Year's, and was like
"Spencer asked me to move in
with him, and I'm, like
thinking about it."
She didn't tell you that?
- No.
- And I know--
That's just really weird
that she wouldn't say
something to me.
I don't think she would move in
with Spencer.
It's way too soon, like,
I know she's crazy in love
but she's not that crazy.
That's so weird.
- Are you done?
- Awkward.
♪ One breath ♪
♪ Too late ♪
♪ And you're gone ♪
♪ For good ♪
♪ It's funny how far it seems ♪
♪ But what could I do ♪
♪ And what would I change ♪
♪ When everything's strange? ♪
♪ And why should I learn
to fly ♪
♪ When I could just hide away ♪
♪ Isn't it strange? ♪♪
[theme music]