- Good morning.
- What are you doing here?
Um, I slept here last night.
Well, that's a first.
I got in a little bit
of a fight with Spencer
so I wanted to stay here.
Hmm.
What about?
He, um, asked me
to move in with him again.
- Do you wanna move in with him?
- 'I don't know.'
I wanna make, like,
a rational decision.
Not like, "Oh, great,
let's just move in."
Like, his whole logic is,
like, "Why wouldn't you
wanna move in with me?
Like, you don't want--"
'Cause, like, people don't just
move in together that soon.
Like, you told me at the
beginning of this relationship
you said, "I will never move in
with someone
unless I've been dating them
for at least two years."
- Yeah.
- 'Like, you said that to me.'
- I know.
- 'I don't know.'
Do you really wanna
change everything
you believe in just because
some guy's pressuring you?
It's not like I don't wanna live
with him 'cause obviously I do.
What is your reasoning
for not moving in with him?
You know, I'm living with you
and I don't want...
You know, to move out,
it's like--
Well, don't let me
be your excuse.
'Cause I mean
you don't even live with me.
I live with your stuff.
♪ New York City
it's got a hold on me ♪
♪ Na na na New York City ♪
♪ You're my destiny I said ♪
♪ New York City ♪
♪ It's do or die ♪
♪ Na na na New York City ♪
♪ Is electrified ♪
♪ I wanna get away
it's all on the line ♪
♪ That's right... ♪♪
- Hey.
- Hi! How are you?
- Good. How are you?
- Good. Nice to see you.
- You too.
- Welcome to the Big Apple.
Thank you.
Is that your resume
and all your things?
- Yeah.
- Come on in.
- Thank you.
- How was your flight?
It was good.
It was easy.
Uh-huh.
- So are you nervous?
- I am nervous.
- Job interviews are so scary.
- Right.
Hi, Whitney.
- Nice to see you again.
- Nice to see you too.
- How are you?
- I'm great. How are you?
- Good. Great. Have a seat.
- Okay.
♪ You see I couldn't live
my life without you ♪
♪ But the sun would grow cold
the sun would grow cold... ♪♪
(Kristen)
'Well, I can't believe that
he gave you that ultimatum.'
I can't believe it either.
After everything
he's done to you, like
I can't believe
you're still with him
and that you're even
considering moving in with him.
I think we're, like, technically
broken up right now.
Because you wouldn't
move in with him?
(Kristen)
What a jerk.
I don't even know.
Does any part of you
wanna really move in with him
and try and like...
I mean, most of me, you know
really wants to
move in and try.
But there's a big part of me
that's just like
"What's the rush?"
I mean, who's the first guys
that you guys lived with?
- Never lived with a guy.
- You've never lived with a guy?
Well, that's 'cause my boyfriend
lives with his brother
and he's obsessed with him
so he's never gonna move out.
Okay. Okay.
I've lived with almost
every boyfriend I've had.
- And?
- It's...
It's not always
a good thing.
I don't know, it's one of those
decisions, you know
where you're like
"How will you ever know
if you're right or wrong?"
How will you ever know
if it's the right decision, or
not unless you do it, you know?
We're your friends. We're gonna
support you no matter what.
But that's why we're giving you
our honest opinion.
I still don't think
you should move in with him.
[rock song playing]
What we look for is that one or
two very special people
who can really know everything
that's happening in LA,
before it happens.
So I would love if you could
give me a little bit of input
into what photographers you
like, what designers you like.
So I have more of a sense
of you, your visual taste.
Okay, Bruce Weber is a favorite
of the magazine as well as mine.
- 'Mario Testino.'
- He's always flattering.
- Yeah, always.
- Girl always looks great.
And what about
designers you love?
Designers I love.
- In love, uh, Balenciaga.
- Mm-hmm.
I love YSL.
I mean, those are obviously
not clothes that I can afford
but just looking at them
and just being
in the presence of them,
is just amazing.
Fantastic. Is this what you
really wanna do, Whitney?
You wanna be a fashion stylist
or a fashion editor?
- You love it? Love clothes?
- Love clothes.
Well, listen, I don't really
have any more questions for you.
You know, we're interviewing
several girls for the job.
- Mm-hmm.
- It's one position.
A lot of competition
but we'll definitely
be in touch with you soon.
- Okay, great.
- Okay nice to see you.
Take care.
Have a safe trip back to LA.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Bye-bye.
[instrumental music]
- Hello?
- 'What up, sweetheart?'
Hey, Spence.
What are you doing?
(Spencer)
'I need you to come meet me.
I mean, uh-uh, we need to talk.'
Why?
(Spencer)
'I can't tell you.
It's a surprise.'
Well, then, maybe I can't go
if you can't tell me.
(Spencer)
'Heidi, come on.
Just meet me.'
'I have a huge surprise
for you.'
Okay, fine.
Where are you?
(Spencer)
'I'll text you the address.
Just come here.'
- Okay.
- 'Come meet me.'
- 'It's gonna be great.'
- Okay. Alright. Bye.'
Where are you goin'?
Um, just a break.
I'll be right back.
♪ I ♪
♪ I know what I'm doin' ♪
♪ Don't tell me
I'm losin' myself ♪
♪ In trade for someone else ♪
♪ I ♪
♪ I know what I'm sayin' ♪
♪ I'm tired of playin'
these games ♪
♪ Over and over and again ♪♪
What's this all about?
A little surprise.
Surprise?
Oh, you're excited to see me.
I was just a little irritated
the other day.
It's a surprise.
Come on.
Drumroll, please.
[imitates drumroll]
Okay, here's your surprise.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
You're already walking past.
We got a skylight right here.
[door closes]
A kitchen.
You don't look too excited.
A little shocked?
I mean, last time I talked,
you were just kind of like
"Get out of my car and..."
I was "Get out of my car"
because--
I know, I just thought...
I was frustrated
with the fact
that we've been arguin'
about this.
Just don't understand
why it's so difficult for you
to not live with Lauren
and come live here.
That's why I got us
this place.
Well, well, it's really nice,
you know.
[sighs]
This is your new bedroom.
You can fit a nice,
uh, California king
right here in the middle.
Check out the balcony, now.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Oh, yes!
All of Hollywood
is right here.
Lookin' down on it.
We got Les Deux
right there.
Blowfish right there.
Got Don Antonio's
way down there.
So you sold?
If I do this with you though
you're gonna be serious, right?
No more messing around,
no playmates, no any of that.
It's just gonna be
me and you here.
- Right?
- Deal.
I don't want any of those things
to happen again, you know?
I want this to be a serious--
A night in the club with a bunch
of girls. It's not like--
I'm just saying
is a night in the club
with a bunch of girls
gonna happen again
if you think
it's no big deal?
Um...it will not
happen again.
Okay.
Promise me that.
Heidi, I swear.
I mean, I'm not trying
to move in with you
for any other reason
than to be with you more.
- It's like...
- Okay.
Let's, um, let's do it.
Let's move in.
- Into this apartment with me?
- Yeah, I'm gonna move in.
[laughs]
Alright. Then, you know, I think
this will be really good.
♪ Even after it all ♪
♪ I wanna make it
beautiful again ♪
♪ Even after it all ♪
♪ I just don't know
right now ♪♪
- Hey.
- 'Hello.'
- 'What are you doing?'
- Just about to leave for work.
Um, I stayed
at Spencer's last night.
Yeah, I figured.
You didn't come home.
- 'Yeah. He-he.'
- I'm assuming you made up?
He was like, "Hey, can you
meet me at this place?"
And I went there,
and he surprised me.
- And there was an apartment.
- He got an apartment?
(Heidi)
'Yeah, he was like, "You can
move in here if you want."'
If I wanna live with him,
then I should.
And, you know,
just like you said, so...
So you're moving out?
Yeah, so...
Okay. Do you know
when you're moving out?
- Um, I think kind of soon.
- Well, you have to let me know.
'Cause I have to start
looking for a new roommate.
I have to let them know
when to move in.
Well, that's exciting,
new roommate
who'll be here all the time.
- Mm-hmm.
- 'Oh, my gosh.'
But the apartment's so nice
and really high ceilings.
It sounds like
everything's perfect.
I know, after a hard year,
it's a...
- It's a good step.
- What could go wrong?
Yeah, so...
I'm gonna go to work.
But congratulations.
[instrumental music]
(Brody)
Damn. You're not movin' out.
You're getting married.
That's basically
what you're sayin'.
No, 'cause if I was getting
married, I'd have to buy a ring.
- And I'm not buying a ring.
- Why even move in?
Why not just keep it the way
it is, live here
and just keep seein' her
like you are?
Why do you have
to move in with her?
'Cause I don't want her
living with Lauren.
'As long as Lauren
is in that girl's life'
we're gonna have fights, 'cause
any time that girl comes around
there's a-automatically
a problem, 'cause she hates me.
Do I gotta, like, plan,
we have to, like plan this
in advance,
when the boys can go out
and party and hang out or...
No, just call the homeboy phone.
It's right here.
- The homeboy phone?
- Got the girlfriend phone.
And I got the homeboy phone.
Just hit that one up,
you're covered.
'I was born a player, dog.
That's what I do.'
I'm not gonna change.
Spencer's Spencer.
- Playboy Spence.
- Still the man.
You are gonna be
out of there so fast.
[laughs]
♪ I know ♪
♪ Well I know all the tricks
in the book ♪
♪ Well I know ♪
♪ Well it's hard for me
to tell ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ Well I know
all the tricks... ♪
[cell phone ringing]
- Hello?
- Whitney.
- Hi. How are you?
- 'I'm okay.'
How's New York?
(Whitney)
'It's so cold here.'
- You okay?
- 'Yeah, I'll be fine.'
So, what's up?
(Whitney)
'So I talked to Heidi and
she gave me official notice'
that she's, like, definitely
moving out now
and moving in with Spencer.
Oh, my gosh.
Are you serious?
- 'Mm-hmm.'
- Oh, my gosh.
(Lauren)
Oh, wait, I forgot to ask you.
How'd your interview go?
I haven't heard anything yet.
We'll see.
I'm sure you did great.
That is so exciting.
'When do you get back?'
Um, I'll be back
tomorrow morning.
'Seriously, call me
the second you come back.'
'I wanna take you
out to dinner.'
- 'Okay. Definitely.'
- Okay, yay.
Have a safe flight.
I'll see you when you get back.
Okay. Bye.
♪ No you ♪
♪ Are not ♪
♪ The only one lonely ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ Are not ♪
♪ The only one lonely ♪♪
Hey.
What are you doing?
Um, just packing.
I'm moving today.
- You're moving today?
- Yeah, today.
I didn't know
you were moving today.
- Yeah, so...
- Wow.
I feel like it's like
a breakup almost.
You know, it's like moving out,
separating our stuff.
Um, I definitely think,
since I'm moving out
I need to make, you know,
more of, like, taco Tuesday
and, like, really
come every Tuesday.
But what's the difference
between you moving out?
You don't do it now
and you live with me.
But, like, I want to make sure
I do, you know?
What I mean is,
the ball's in your court.
If you wanna make an effort,
that's fine.
I don't want it
to be like I move out
and that's the end of it,
it's not like that at all.
It might be, though, Heidi.
You're with someone
you really love
'and, like, I'm-I'm really glad
that you're happy.'
But you're not gonna
be able to have both
when you move in with him.
'I mean, it sucks
and it makes me sad'
because, like,
you were my best friend
that I moved here with, but...
Well, I'd like to still try
to make an effort so...
- But really make one.
- Okay.
I mean, it's nice to hear.
It's just, like, we'll see.
Ah, ha-ha.
Let's rock and roll.
Well, let me know if you need
help in your apartment.
- Yeah, for sure.
- Okay.
Yeah.
And you know,
you can always come back.
I mean, you know,
I hope this works
but I'm saying,
if it doesn't...
Yeah. Okay, well,
I guess I'll get going.
- Okay. I love you.
- I love you.
Okay.
[instrumental music]
What's wrong?
You look so serious.
You won't regret this.
I promise you.
This is the best choice ever.
- You ready to go?
- Yeah, let's go.
- Sure?
- Yeah.
♪ Save me ♪
♪ Save me from this
lonely place where ♪
♪ All the things
that matter inside ♪
♪ Are fading ♪
♪ But take me ♪
♪ Take me to another
place where ♪
♪ All the things that matter ♪
♪ Inside won't fade ♪
♪ Away ♪♪
[pop song playing]
Oh, my God.
Your hair looks so good.
- Do you like it?
- I love it.
- Really?
- It looks so pretty.
Thank you.
It was a big change.
Yeah, for sure.
That's a life-changing thing.
- Yeah, no kidding.
- Oh, my God.
- How are you?
- Good.
Speaking of life-changing,
um...
- Yeah?
- I moved in with Spencer.
After all my grown-up
advice to you
and you didn't do
what I said?
Because it was like
the advice I needed to hear
to make the decision I did.
You know, it's like,
I'm really happy though.
And I'm gonna cook him
dinner tonight.
Like our first. I've never
cooked for him before.
- It's like our first--
- Have you ever cooked dinner?
- No.
- Oh, my gosh.
- What are you cooking?
- I know.
I think pasta,
or something easy.
I mean, do you even have all
of the equipment to cook with?
Oh, my God.
No, I have to go get it.
- What's it called?
- Dinner.
- No.
- What? Pasta? What?
The equipment to cook, like.
Oh, pots and pans.
Yeah, yeah.
I have to go get all that.
Oh, okay, well,
good luck with that.
And good luck
with dinner tonight.
Thank you. If I need anything,
or the kitchen's on fire
I'm calling you.
Alright, sounds good.
Bye.
(Heidi)
'Bye.'
[instrumental music]
♪ Everything has changed ♪
♪ Nothing's quite the same ♪
♪ The world I knew so well ♪
♪ Is under
a brand-new spell... ♪♪
- Hey, roomie.
- Surprise.
- You have pizza and champagne?
- Mm-hmm. Best combo ever.
- How was your day at work?
- It was good. It was.
You've already moved, like,
chairs and stuff in here.
I know. I only got two
of my chairs.
And there's boxes everywhere.
I brought us
a very elegant dinner.
I love it.
It's to celebrate
our first night
together as roommates.
Oh, you're so nice.
Do it that way, Lauren.
- Whoo!
- Oh, my God!
[screams]
Oh, my God.
All my boxes are wet.
[laughs]
♪ Nothing ventured
nothing gained ♪
I definitely think
I made the right choice.
I can promise
you made the right choice.
[laughs]
- I love you.
♪ Waiting for the other shoe
to drop ♪
It's kinda weird though.
Like, not having Heidi
in our apartment anymore.
But you know, I have another
great friend to live with
and I'm sure she's really happy
so...good for her.
What if she breaks up
with Spencer
and comes back and she expects
everything to be the same?
But you know what?
It kind of would be.
I think you moving out
is gonna be the best thing
for your guys'
relationship ever.
I feel like one day without
Heidi makes me go crazy.
Lauren's gotta be going
crazy without you.
- Toast.
- Cheers.
To my new roommate.
There's no one
I'd rather live with.
Aww. Cheers.
I'm still a little mad that it
took you this long to move in.
You know, I made
a rule for myself.
And I wasn't gonna move in
with anyone
that I hadn't been
in a relationship with
for, like, two years.
So...
Don't make me
regret this, Spencer.
♪ 'Cause it feels like ♪
♪ Everything is gonna
turn out fine ♪
♪ Yeah a change
is gonna come ♪
♪ 'Cause it feels
like this time ♪
♪ I've crossed the other side ♪
♪ And it's gonna be alright ♪♪
[instrumental music]