Oh my God, you are not gonna
guess what happened to me on New
Year's.
You kissed a boy.
Um, no.
Spencer asked me
to move in with him.
(Lauren)
'Yeah, Lo told me.'
I was surprised you told Lo
before me though.
It's kind of, like,
big news.
Well, I'd just found out.
Thought it was really
nice of him to...
You know, that he wanted
that but--
That kinda freaks me out.
I gotta be honest.
- No, it's nice.
- 'Yeah.'
I think if a guy
after a few months asked me
to move in with him,
I would be like, "Whoa."
Yeah.
It was sweet.
Do you want to?
Um...
I told him that I wasn't
going to, so...
I'm happy that I decided
to stay here with you though.
Me too, I'm not
like about to celebrate
'my 21st birthday
with a different roommate.'
A good roommate, that's like
a good pair of jeans.
You know what I mean?
Like, you hang on to those.
- 'You do.'
- No matter what.
You do.
That's very true.
♪ She goes to California ♪
♪ Oh California's not so far ♪
♪ When I close my eyes
and wonder where you are ♪♪
- Hello. How are you?
- Hey, what are you doing?
- What's going on?
- Just relaxing.
- What are you up to today?
- Nice.
Nothing much.
Oh, my gosh.
Is everything's set
for Lauren's surprise party?
Yeah.
Everything's set. Ouch.
We have, um, Hyde
the guest list, the cake.
She knows her birthday
is coming up.
And she thinks it's just you
and her going to dinner?
So maybe if I bailed out,
like, right before dinner?
- It will throw--
- She'll be so mad at you.
She'll be like, "I can't
believe you're leaving."
And I'll be like,
"I'm sorry. I have to go."
And then, like,
it will really throw off.
And then you swoop in
and like...
And then I'll bring her
and I'll just keep texting you.
- Yeah, and just be like--
- Well, I'll tell her...
I'll just be like, "Yeah, you
know, let's go meet my sister
"and let's go meet
some of my friends at Hyde
and have a couple drinks
since you're 21."
- Yeah, exactly. Exactly.
- And we'll walk off.
And then she's gonna get
so mad, Heidi.
Can you imagine
if that really happened?
That would be
the worst person ever.
- That would be so mean.
- 'I know.'
But it is gonna be so good.
She's gonna die.
- Yeah.
- 'Yeah.'
[rock music playing]
Lucky brand...
Short-sleeved sweatshirt.
Orange.
Hey, isn't it your birthday
this weekend?
Mm-hmm. My 21st.
- Your big 21st.
- I'm so excited.
(Whitney)
'What are you gonna do?'
Um...I don't know.
I mean...
I've already told Heidi
I'd go out to dinner with her.
But, I mean, we'll probably
go out afterwards.
- Yeah.
- I haven't really planned it.
I always kind of thought
I'd have a big 21st but--
Yeah. I didn't really
have a big 21st.
It's one of those things
that just being 21 is enough.
You don't really even need
to have any sort of party.
But I always thought, like,
I would have this huge party
and it just kind of, like,
came really fast.
- You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
I mean I'm kinda like, um...
You don't really have to know
what you're gonna do.
As long as you have your
friends by your side.
- Yeah.
- That's what matters.
Oh, my God.
But 21 is such a big one.
I know.
I'm so excited.
Hey, Spencer.
Hey, so, um,
I got Hyde for Sunday night
for Lauren's surprise
birthday party, and, um...
Yeah, it'll be great.
It'll be like 60 people.
So bring Brody, too.
[laughs]
Okay, I love you.
Bye.
Hi.
Here, let's go inside.
- Hi.
Hi.
I can't really talk to you.
I'm kind of at work.
- What?
- I'm at work.
- I can't really talk to you.
- Okay.
- That's fine.
- I'm so busy. So what's up?
Uh, I just wanted to see
how you were and everything
'cause I haven't talked
to you in so long.
What's going on?
Nothin'.
Just working a lot.
And I've been so, so busy,
crazy running around.
- Yeah.
- How's school?
Good, but I haven't, like,
talked to Lauren at all
and so I just wanted to, like,
see what was going on with that.
- Yeah.
- I don't know.
Do you think she's ready
to talk at all or not?
No. I don't think she wants
to talk for a while.
I haven't talked to my best
friend of 15 years for, like
what, three weeks
for what, sloppy thirds?
Like, that's...crazy!
I think that's why
she's all mad
'because it was like a code
that you don't hook up'
'with your friends' exes
or, like, past hook-ups.'
One night should not
have even amounted
to two days of this fight
and I think we both agree
on how crazy out of proportion
this got blown. Like--
Well, I told you,
and I told her
I was, like,
that's between you guys
and I want nothing
to do with it. So...
Okay. That's fine.
I mean, it's like
an awkward situation.
- I know. It's so awkward.
- It's so weird, I'm like...
- Yeah.
- Thought, like, I don't know--
- Busy, busy.
- What?
- I said busy, busy.
- Yeah.
- You have to go back to work?
I'm doing, like,
a lot of office stuff.
- Okay.
- Right, so...
I mean, maybe another place,
another time.
I just, like,
haven't been able to really
like, get a hold
of anyone, so I figured
I'd just see
what was going on.
Okay, well,
have a good day at work.
Okay. Bye.
Well, yeah.
♪ Assuming you can't run away ♪
♪ Do your best
to hide your face ♪
♪ And oh I know you best ♪
♪ I know you get
what you're getting ♪
♪ Or you get what you deserve ♪♪
Hi.
Are you reading?
I'm reading "You Didn't
Hear It From Us."
Oh, my gosh.
Uh, guess who showed up
at my work, uninvited.
- Who?
- Jen Bunney.
I go, "I think it's really
inappropriate
that you're at my work.
I don't know what happened."
I was like "With you and Lauren,
it's between you and Lauren.
Please don't talk
to me about it."
I go, "Obviously,
you know, you did wrong.
Give her space and don't come
back to my work place."
Like, "Don't be so desperate.
"Do you not have any other
friends? Like, chill out.
I said, I'll talk to you
when I wanna talk to you."
I was friends with her
'cause you're friends with her.
- You know what I mean?
- Mm-hmm.
I told her just
to give you your space.
(Lauren)
'That's all I need,
like, honestly...'
Like, if you do
a really bad thing
or if you do
a really shady thing
be like, "I was shady."
Like, just fess up to it.
That's fine. I don't need
people like that in my life.
You know what I mean, like,
I have too many good people
in my life to try
and have bad ones in it, too.
We're still on for your
birthday dinner, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Done.
[rock music]
♪ Go ♪♪
Twenty-one. So exciting.
What time are
our reservations?
Like, 8:30.
Are you wearing a dress?
No, I'm gonna wear,
um, jeans and a top.
- What are you gonna wear?
- Should I not wear a dress?
- I have a dress on.
- You're the birthday girl.
You should be wearing
dresses all week.
♪ I'm so excited ♪♪
[cell phone ringing]
Hey, Spence. What's up?
'Why? What's wrong?'
'Are you okay?
What do you mean?'
Right now?
'I mean, come on, seriously?'
Heidi, who are you talking to?
Spencer, are you sure?
'Alright. Fine.
I'll call you in 20.'
'Okay, bye.'
[sighs]
Um...
What...
Spencer just called
and I'm really sorry,
but I have to go.
I'll call you when I know what's
going on or what it is, so...
- Okay.
'I-I-I'm really
sorry, Lauren.'
- H-Heidi?
- 'I love you.'
You made plans with me to do
something for my birthday.
I know, but I don't know
what's wrong.
Well, then call him and say,
"I'm gonna go to dinner
with my best friend
for her birthday."
'Like don't, like, stop
leaving me for Spencer.'
- 'Stop.'
- I'll call you.
[instrumental music]
[door closes]
[sighs]
[cell phone rings]
- Hello?
- Oh, my God.
- She totally bought it.
- It's gonna be fun.
Should I bring her... I'll bring
her, like, at 9:15-ish.
Perfect.
She totally won't know.
Okay, bye.
[cell phone rings]
- Hello?
- Hey. What are you doing?
Hi. Nothing.
Well, Heidi just left here
and she was like, "Oh, Spencer
just called me and da-da-da."
And she's like, "I can't.
I need to go.
Can we do this later?"
Um, well, come over
and I'll take you out.
Okay, bye.
[rock music]
(Heidi)
'Uh, excuse me.
Could I have your attention?'
'Lauren's gonna be here
in, like, two minutes'
so if we can all, like,
jump out and say "Surprise"
'cause it's a surprise
party, so...
Thank you. You can go back
to your things now.
[instrumental music]
She just told you and left you?
- Like, she didn't say--
- Yeah. No.
It was like,
"He won't talk to me."
I have to talk to him in person.
Sorry. I have to go."
And she was really
short about it.
Then she just left.
Kinda, like, "You've got
to be kidding me."
Like, "You're not actually
doing this, are you?"
And she was, like,
"I'm sorry. I have to go."
It's like three strikes
and you're out.
No, she's on, like,
her 10th strike.
[music continues]
- They're here, they're here.
- Shh. Shh.
One, two, and three.
(all)
Surprise!
Happy birthday!
[all cheering]
Surprise!
- Happy birthday!
- Hi!
Thank you.
[hip-hop music]
There is the oh-so-beautiful
birthday girl.
- Yes.
- How are you?
- Good. How are you?
- Everything good?
- Oh, yeah, really?
- Yeah.
I know.
And then I went
on a couple of dates.
Come here.
[hip-hop music]
- We doing the birthday toast?
- Birthday toast!
- Spratt, give the speech.
- Okay.
- Speech, speech, speech!
- Alright.
Okay, I'm not
very good at speeches
'cause Lo said
I'm not very smart
but I do know this.
Heidi, the love of my life
loves Lauren more
than anything in the world.
'So that makes Lauren
an amazing person.'
'We don't see
eye to eye, but they do.'
So at the end of the day,
we all see eye to eye.
- Cheers.
- Happy birthday.
- You're amazing.
- Cheers.
Twenty-one, it's a big deal.
♪ And I know ♪
♪ What it feels to be alive ♪
♪ And if you breathe for me ♪
♪ I'll breathe for you tonight ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
♪ Tonight... ♪♪
♪ You're a distraction ♪
♪ For my eyes to realize ♪
♪ It's my attraction
that makes me keep coming back ♪
♪ There's something about you
that I can't hold in my hand ♪
♪ And my control
is what you can't understand ♪
♪ Yeah yeah ♪♪
Did you have fun?
Yeah, it was really fun.
How was his birthday toast
to me?
- He was like--
- It was pretty.
"Me and Lauren
don't always see eye to eye
but I see eye to eye
with Heidi."
I was like, "Just say
happy birthday."
[laughs]
Seriously, I was,
like, just be like
"Happy birthday, Lauren,"
and it's done.
He's a big toaster.
What else?
No Jen Bunney talk?
Nope.
No Jen Bunney.
Shh.
She was, like, telling someone,
like, she's like
"Oh, we'll make up by her
birthday, so I'll be there."
I'm like,
"Don't come to my birthday."
[laughs]
A lot of people don't like her.
That's cra... Why is that?
She's kind of,
like, had a lot
of problems with girls
and their guys.
- Really?
- Like, hooked up with exes.
Or, um, lied to them
about things they've said.
- Or just, oh...
- Change of subject here.
Um...
Oh, that's not weird
for you.
No, it's not weird.
Did you know
that the night I kissed Jason
Jen kissed him first?
I told Jen,
"I-I kind of like Jason."
And she's like, "I got
your back, I got your back."
She went into another room
to talk to him.
- Apparently made out with him.
- What?
And then he went
and kissed me.
- Shut up.
- Yeah.
That whole situation could have
been completely avoided.
She just had to be,
like, an honest person to me
and she wasn't,
you know what I mean?
And you're supposed
to be best friends.
And we're supposed
♪ Oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh ♪
♪ 'Cause this is a battle ♪
♪ And it's your final
last call ♪
[doorbell rings]
♪ It was a trial ♪
♪ You made a mistake we know ♪
♪ Can't you see
you've hurt me so ♪
♪ Why aren't you sorry? ♪
♪ Why? ♪
Hey. Can I come in and talk
with you about everything?
♪ 'Cause this is a battle ♪
♪ This is a battle ♪
♪ Oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh ♪♪
(Lauren)
'Okay, so, say to me
whatever you want to say'
because you obviously feel
like you need to say something.
Well...
I just have been trying, like,
really hard to talk to you.
I know. Well, I'm saying, like,
you've tried, really tried.
So, like, talk to me now.
Okay, well...
[sighs]
I just feel like everything
got so blown out of proportion
than what it needed to be,
like--
I don't feel
that way at all but--
Okay, that's the way I feel
and not necessarily, like,
the situation--
(Lauren)
'It probably feels
that way to you'
'cause it didn't
happen to you.
I just think that
what you don't understand
is that I really never
meant to hurt you.
I-I don't think
you meant to hurt me.
I don't think that you
thought about me
at all when you were doing it.
Because you were only
thinking about yourself.
- I wasn't thinking.
- You really like didn't think?
Like it wasn't even a thought
in your head when you left?
No, I'm gonna be perfectly
honest with you.
I knew that Brody was trying
to hook up with me.
But you know what, it shouldn't
even have been a situation.
You shouldn't be in a situation
where you're, you know
hitting on some guy that
I could have been interested.
You know what,
it wasn't just any guy.
It wasn't who he was,
it was the fact
that that was
the first guy
that I was able to have
a crush on after Jason.
- That was a big deal to me.
- Okay.
It had to be that guy.
I didn't know Brody
even mattered.
(Lauren)
'Brody doesn't matter.'
'It's not...
I'm not mad about Brody!'
- This is about a guy.
- No.
It's about the fact that you
did something really shady
and you did it behind my back
and you were evil and conniving.
It wasn't all Brody.
It was you!
'And it was, like, I didn't
need my best friend to go'
'and make me feel
like an idiot'
like I've had happen
to me before.
And it just sucked that it
wasn't some girl I hated.
No, it was my best friend
who made me feel
like such an idiot
and made me feel so low.
It was a mistake.
- I messed up one night.
- I know you did.
- That's why, I'm sayin'--
- No, no, no.
You made a mistake
that you went home with him.
that you kissed him
and you stared in my eyes
and lied to me about it.
Then you made a mistake
that you tried to
blame it on every person
you could.
I'm not trying
to play the victim.
(Lauren)
'You are, you sit there
and you, like'
make your sad puppy-dog face.
You're like,
"Oh, it's so hard."
You put yourself
in this situation.
And I've tried to apologize to
you so much.
Sincerely sorry.
I understand what I did
was wrong. Really, really wrong.
You've screwed up a lot
of friendships because of guys.
The first night
that I told you I liked Jason
and I wanted to kiss him,
you went and kissed him.
- Don't even go there.
- 'Yes, you did.'
- That was--
- 'It doesn't matter.'
You didn't tell me that night.
That was, like,
a joke, Lauren.
- Come on. You can't--
- It's funny.
It's funny 'cause I dated him
for a year after.
I obviously didn't have
any feelings for him.
I know I made a mistake
and I know I lied to you
and I am so sorry.
I've been burned by so many
friends, especially lately.
And I really am starting to
learn who my true friends are.
'And I have every reason
not to trust you.'
You know it's true.
I'm sorry I hurt you.
I appreciate that.
Thank you.
Nothin',
there's nothing I can do?
There's nothing I can say?
No.
- Just like...
I think you've done
and said enough.
♪ In so many words ♪
♪ I wish I could explain ♪
♪ But it won't sound the same ♪
♪ If promises... ♪
So I'll let you call me
when you're ready.
♪ It's a little too late ♪
♪ I'm under the spell ♪
♪ And I can't hear
you saying good-bye ♪
♪ Good-bye ♪
♪ Good-bye good-bye good-bye ♪♪