Yeah, my * * * golf clubs.
[sighs]
There's so much stuff.
These aren't my towels.
- 'What else is there?'
- That's it.
- That's mine.
- You're my...
Now, what am I supposed
to do with all this?
I'm sorry,
I just didn't wanna be like
dropping your stuff off
on the curb.
That's not how I saw it.
Stop. Come here.
[sniffles]
'Are you still gonna
be my buddy?'
I can't be a normal buddy
though. It doesn't work.
- Why?
- I can't 'cause it's you.
So what do you want me to do?
I don't understand you.
I'm saying I don't want you
out of my life.
I don't wanna be like, no, I'm
never gonna talk to you again
but I can't be normal with you.
Like, I want to, but I can't.
It's not that easy to,
like, like, not see you.
I know, but it's harder
to see you.
It just is.
- Come here.
- I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Alright.
♪ But you won't love me anyway ♪
♪ Doesn't matter what I say ♪
♪ To change your mind ♪
♪ I gave it everything I could ♪
♪ But you never ever would ♪
♪ So there you go
for the last time ♪♪
♪ This town is our town ♪
♪ It is so glamorous ♪
♪ I bet you'd live here
if you could and be one of us ♪
♪ This town is our town
it is so glamo... ♪♪
- 'Who are we waiting for?'
- 'Brian.'
Okay, so, Thursday,
as you guys know
Area is our new club
that's opening.
We wanted to do like
an old-school Hollywood opening.
Red carpet and, like, media
and just, you know, really
exciting. And we're way behind.
We're praying to God that
we can get ready by Thursday.
'So, Heidi, you're gonna
be working hostess.'
Rob, door.
Michelle, camera check.
So, Heidi, we've got a lot
of work to do, so don't bug me.
'Alright. Go, team.'
[cell phone rings]
(Heidi on voicemail)
'You've reached Heidi.'
'Leave me a message
and I'll call you back.'
Hey, Heidi. It's Audrina.
Um, I don't know what's going on
or if you're mad at me or what
so call me back whenever
you get this. Bye.
♪ Today will be yesterday ♪
♪ Uh-huh tomorrow ♪
♪ Uh-huh uh-huh tomorrow ♪
♪ Today will be yesterday ♪
♪ Uh-huh tomorrow ♪
♪ Uh-huh uh-huh tomorrow ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪♪
- Hey.
- Hi. How are you?
- I'm great. How are you?
- Good.
What's going on?
Nothing. I just got here
little bit ago.
So what's going on?
How was your summer?
It was good. How was yours?
Um, mine was great.
- I got to go to Paris.
- 'I know.'
- How was it?
- 'It was insane.'
I mean, it was one of
the coolest things, like...
- Oh, my God. Cute purse.
- Oh, thank you.
They had all
these couture dresses
from the last runway shows.
See, like, I worked on
this photo-shoot this summer.
- How cool.
- Yeah. And how was your summer?
Did you end up
getting that beach house?
- I didn't ask you about that.
- Yeah, but not for that long.
Like, I knew
you and Jason broke up
but I didn't even
know what happened.
Like, we just kept fighting
every single day
and it was like the same fights
and we both knew
we were gonna break up.
Are you okay now?
I'm sorry.
So I don't know.
I wonder what we're doing today.
Have you seen Lisa yet?
Just briefly said hi to her,
but I haven't, like
sat down and talked to her
or anything.
I, like, haven't even talked
to her since the Paris thing.
- Really?
- Oh, so real.
Oh, Brent is calling.
Hello.
Yeah. Sure. Okay.
We got to go into Lisa's office.
- Oh, right now?
- Yeah.
[sighs]
Hi, Whitney. Hi, Lauren.
How are you?
- 'Good. How are you?'
- Good.
- 'Welcome back.'
- Thank you.
- Has school started yet?
- 'Yeah.'
I've been in school
for a month already.
And, Lauren,
are you back at FIDM?
Um, I start really soon.
- How was the summer?
- 'Summer was great.'
- Um, Paris was amazing.
- Did you meet Fiona?
I met Fiona.
She was unbelievable.
She sent us
to Coco Chanel's apartment.
We got to see that,
so it was pretty amazing.
Well, that was a great choice
of yours to make to go to Paris.
Is it something
that you think that you might
be interested
in doing next summer?
Definitely. It would be awesome
if I could do that.
Oh, I'm sure we'll have
a conversation and discuss that.
- 'Okay.'
- Lauren didn't go to Paris.
She's gonna always be known as
the girl who didn't go to Paris.
'Do you regret that decision?'
How was your summer at the beach
with your boyfriend?
Did that work out for you?
♪ Oh this is me ♪♪
(Lauren)
'Today was such a bad day.'
'I'm so over hearing
about Paris and Jason.'
[exhales deeply]
I think every day it will get
a little bit easier, you know.
[sniffles]
It is so frustrating
'cause I was just
I broke up with him,
'cause I was sad
of crying every day.
Like, I didn't
wanna cry anymore.
And then I was crying
'cause I was fighting
and now I'm crying 'cause
he's not here to make me stop.
He was like my best friend
and it's like losing
your best friend.
The best part of Jason was you.
'There's just so many guys
who just think'
'you're the most amazing thing
in the entire world.'
I've had so many guys ask me
"Is she single yet?
Is she single yet?"
Like, I'm not kidding.
I hate being single.
I'm not good at it.
♪ He's still here ♪
♪ And I'm gone ♪♪
♪ She said she'd wait
outside the windowsill ♪
(Heidi)
'How do you ever
find this place?'
'This is, like,
in the middle of nowhere.'
This is my spot. I've been here
eating since I was, like, 14.
♪ So I jumped into my car ♪
Bro, should I just
leave the keys in?
♪ Went in to take a look ♪
♪ I bought a long stem rose ♪
Get ready
for the best Mexican food
you ever had
in your entire life.
(Heidi)
'I'm so hungry.'
- So we can draw.
- Yes.
Oh, now we're talking.
Thank you.
- Spencer steak?
- Come on, now.
You don't think they'd give me
my own steak here.
Are you excited about
the Area grand opening?
- A little.
- How do you call that work?
Putting on a walkie-talkie
and cruising around the club?
- It's so fun.
- That's what I'm saying.
It's like the best job
I ever heard of.
Everybody's gonna be there
Thursday night.
Audrina, she's not gonna
be there, no, way. She--
All the people I work
with hate her, so...
You know what she used
to say, right?
She said,
"Oh, Heidi doesn't like me
because I'm hanging out
with Spencer."
When was she... I didn't
hang out with her this summer.
That's what she said.
Was she hitting on you?
No, she was totally,
like, a friend vibe.
- You know?
- She's so weird.
There are some people
in LA that are...
[whistles]
Oh, this margarita
is just too good.
I couldn't be happier right now.
- With your margaritas?
- No.
With Heidi Montag at dinner
at my favorite restaurant
in the world.
That is why
I couldn't be happier.
Thanks for the flowers,
Spencer.
- Are you staying over?
- Yeah.
- Hi. Hi, Bella. Good morning!
- Good morning to you.
- Breakfast without me?
- Yeah, you want some Pinkberry?
- No, thanks.
'Did you have fun with Spencer
last night?'
Oh, my God,
Spencer's getting like
more and more,
like, affectionate too.
- Really?
- Okay.
You know how before it was
like he'll go talk to girls?
He'd be like,
Oh, this is my friend
but he'll keep talking to them.
Now he'll like start,
like, hiding behind me.
He'll be, like,
in a cute way, he'll be like
Oh, yeah. Hi. Nice to see you.
And then he'll, like, run to me
and be like, and this is Heidi
and then he'll like turn to me
and start talking to me.
Oh, Spencer loves you.
♪ Gonna teach you how ♪
♪ To get the girl
of your dreams ♪
(Audrina)
'Thank you.'
Let me get this for you,
my dear.
Thank you.
These are so pretty.
[sighs]
'So, you know, I went out
with Heidi last night.'
I thought you guys were friends.
So did I. I don't know
what her problem is.
And I tried to confront her
about it
and she won't talk to me, so...
Does Lauren have attitude too?
Since Heidi doesn't like me
for whatever reason
they're kind of
into their own thing.
How do you not like you?
That's what I wanna know.
- I don't know.
- 'So, I'm gonna ask her.'
They live together, right?
- 'So it's like two against--'
- Two against me.
- I'll be your team member.
- Thank you.
I got your back.
I gotta take you to-- Do you
like Mexican food though?
- It's my favorite.
- We're going to Don Antonio's.
Like, life-changing
Mexican food.
- Like, unheard of.
- So good?
Patron margaritas
on the rocks, pitchers.
'What do you say
we cruise tonight'
'and then we roll to Area?'
- Yeah.
- Are you guys cool?
I'm still gonna go.
I'm not afraid or like...
- You know?
- It's not like she--
'Heidi doesn't wanna
be friends, that's fine'
but I'm still gonna go
and have fun.
[pop music]
[indistinct chatter]
- Yeah?
- What?
Is Cody here with this person
or is he coming--
Yeah, I don't know
if he's with her.
Kristen, come in.
Hi.
- What are you doing?
- Coming to dance.
Are you having fun?
You working out here?
Yeah. Lots to do. Lots to do.
- Where's our table?
- On the dance floor.
Dance floor where? You're not
gonna show us our table?
- No. Sorry. It's VIP.
- I get you.
- Have fun out here though.
- Alright, bye.
(Heidi)
'Why would she show up here
with him?'
Doesn't she have her own
friends? Like, can't she get--
She's obviously doing it
to get a rise out of you.
Let me tell you something, girls
are sometimes
worse than the guys.
L, she and I have beef.
Oh, wow.
What?
Heidi.
- Let's go.
- 'Okay.'
Why would she come here with a
guy that I was hooking up with?
I would never do that.
I would never disrespect
somebody like that.
Because you're a good girl.
And then you know
she's playing around, like
"I'm a nice girl.
No, you're not.
You're a mean,
conniving bitch."
Girls like that
are not worth it.
So how are things?
How's the boy situation?
Non-existent right now.
With Spencer? What happened?
- 'He showed up with Audrina.'
- Shut up.
- Where?
- At Area.
While you were working?
Oh, my God.
What, were you guys full-on
together in a relationship?
I think it was gonna
start to be and then--
Like, you were definitely
falling for him?
Yeah.
- Oh, God. That sucks.
- I think I'm gonna go home.
- I really don't feel good.
- Really? Why?
I don't know, I've been
like so incredibly dizzy
and nauseous for the past couple
days that I can't even stand up.
I can't even, like, sit.
I'm so like...
- Okay. I'm sorry.
- I know. Me too.
- Okay. Bye, honey.
- Bye.
The girl I told you about,
Heidi, we used to be friends.
I went to Area grand opening.
So does she, like,
she works there?
She, she helps out at the door.
And we walked in with the guy
that she's, like
madly in love with, and like,
he kind of had a crush on me
and like, I don't know,
I think she just freaked out.
'Cause she's like, "Oh, my God,
why is she here with him?"
'Like, I don't,
I don't like him.'
I have no interest
in any of her guys.
And he came up to me
and he kept grabbing me
on the dance floor
and I was like, Spencer, stop.
So he likes you,
but Heidi likes him?
Listen to this, he got back
with Heidi supposedly
and I was like, "Aren't you
back with Heidi now?"
And he's like,
"Well, not tonight."
I was like it's so piggish.
And so, I don't know,
it's just like a huge ordeal.
- And it's just stupid.
- Drama.
She should just get over it.
♪ I came home
in the middle of the night ♪
♪ My father says what you gonna
do with your life? ♪
♪ Well daddy dear ♪
Have a good day.
Ah, that's okay. Thanks.
♪ Oh girls
they wanna have fun ♪
- Hi.
♪ Take a beautiful girl ♪
♪ Oh and they hide her away
from the rest of the world ♪
♪ Well not me ♪
♪ I wanna be the one
in the sun ♪
♪ Girls they wanna have fun ♪
♪ Oh girls they ♪
♪ It's all they really want ♪
♪ Those girls ♪
♪ They wanna have fun ♪
♪ Those girls
they wanna have fun ♪♪
[theme music]