(Audrina)
'So, what's going on
with you and Heidi?'
You guys are working on your
friendship now, aren't you?
The way we get along is we
just don't talk about Spencer.
I mean,
she doesn't say his name.
We just don't talk about him,
and it's awkward
'cause he's obviously,
a really big part of her life.
I mean, she is with him
every night.
She spends way more time
with him than me
so it's, like, kinda weird.
I don't know what he did,
it's like he put a spell
on her or something,
or she's just, like
'head over heels for this guy.'
I don't know. It's weird.
You know what I mean?
Like, I still, I don't like him.
I don't wanna be around him.
Do they say,
"I love you," and stuff?
Already?
She's making the same mistake
she did with Jordan, kind of.
That was the day, like,
she made such a big deal.
She was, like,
with Jordan, she was like
"I will never, I always
will have at least one night
a week where
I stay away from them"
and like,
she stayed at our apartment
like twice this month.
Oh, my God.
But, it kinda bums me out,
when she's like
"Let's plan a Lauren
and Heidi day."
And I'm like, "Every day used to
be Lauren and Heidi day."
Wow.
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I'd do it all over again ♪
♪ I'd do it all... ♪♪
Thank you so much
for coming with me.
Any time.
'Any excuse
to spend more time with you.'
(Heidi)
'Oh! So nice.'
Do you think that Lauren
would be upset at all
if I hung out
with you and Spencer?
Lauren can't control
your life, Jen.
No, she doesn't control my life.
I control my life, Heidi.
- Exactly, so you can hang--
- Exactly.
Exactly, you can
hang out with me
'if you wanna hang out with me.'
I just don't wanna do anything
that would upset her.
I just bought these.
Well, you can't live
your life like that either.
Like, do what you wanna do.
I'm trying
to listen to you, Heidi.
I'm trying to take
your advice, as usual.
As usual, I'm right.
What do I want,
what do I want?
♪ This is your wake-up call ♪
♪ You better watch your back ♪
♪ When you're living in
Spy town ♪
♪ No more fun and games ♪
♪ They know your every move ♪
♪ When you're living in
Spy town... ♪♪
- Hello.
- How are you today?
- I'm good. How are you?
- You look cute.
- Oh, thank you.
I'm, like, in jammies today.
I was, I wore this
to class this morning
and then I just added
this nice little touch.
It's very cute.
It's, uh, Jen's birthday today.
It is?
- How old is she?
- Twenty-one.
- Ooh!
- 'I know.'
I'm, like, excited
to celebrate it with Jen
because, like,
we've been best friends.
- Since, like, third grade.
- I know.
And she's been really great
'cause, like, Heidi's been
so, like, involved with--
Yeah, she's been
gone all the time, so Jen's
like, basically, been,
like, living with me.
'Yeah.'
She's been
a really good friend.
That's really nice.
Is she having a party?
'Uh, yeah,
we were all going out.'
She already invited
Spencer, though.
She did?
The only good thing is that if
Spencer comes he brings Brody.
[laughs]
That's my plus.
That's a plus.
I guess that's worth it, right?
You got to make some sacrifices
for the good of your...self.
[laughs]
♪ I'm never satisfied ♪
♪ Yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ Never satisfied... ♪♪
Look at Hollywood Star tours.
Pratt,
that should be your new job.
[chuckles]
What, giving star tours?
I was always thinkin' I would be
so amazing at doing star maps.
'Cause I feel
like we could, like, hit up
all the homies spots, like,
give very little directions.
[girls giggling]
God, I-I'm in such habit
of just seeing a girl laugh
and like hitting on her, but
I'm always like "Girlfriend."
I don't know when are you
you gotta find a lady, now
that I've got a girlfriend
you need a girlfriend
so we can double date.
Heidi's tryin' to get us a roll
to, um, Jen Bunney's
birthday at Les Deux.
I like little Bunney.
She's-she's a cutie pie.
'I think you should mack Jen,
to be honest. Jen is cute.'
Tell you how
to get in the back door.
[laughing]
♪ I wanna party all night ♪
♪ We're gonna make it happen ♪
♪ Make it happen yeah ♪
♪ I wanna party ♪
♪ Party all night night night ♪
♪ We're gonna make it happen ♪
♪ Come on and party ♪
♪ Party all night... ♪♪
Elizabeth,
you like sushi, right?
- Yes.
- These are really good.
Heaven roll's really good, the
Hollywood roll is really good.
'We'll just order
a bunch of rolls.'
♪ Hey hey hey ♪
♪ I like your outfit ♪
♪ Your sh-sh-sh-shoes
and your... ♪♪
(Heidi)
Happy birthday!
I'm so glad you came.
- Hi! How are you?
- Hi.
- You look pretty.
- Thank you, you look great.
Hi! Hi! Hi!
- Yes
Yay!
To Jen
one of my oldest friends
in the World
who has always been there
for me, no matter what.
Hello! Whoo!
Here's to Jen's
21st birthday
and for us,
a decade of friendship.
Cheers! Girl's night! Whoo!
- Best friends.
Heidi, when should we
give it to her?
- Now or after? Okay. Now.
- 'Now. Now! Now! Now!'
This one is just
'cause it's your 21st birthday
so it's very
21st birthday appropriate.
(Heidi)
Yay!
Yeah, 21!
(Jen)
'Done and done.'
[instrumental music]
♪ You want to be my lover ♪
♪ You want to call me
baby doll ♪
♪ You're never gonna do ♪
♪ Better than me no ♪
♪ Better than me ♪
♪ You see you want me ♪
♪ To be your... ♪♪
[indistinct chattering]
Whoo-ho!
Hey.
Yay! I'm so glad you're here.
- Hi.
Yay!
- Whoo! Yay!
- Bunney.
I know.
Shut up.
Snuggle up.
One, two, three.
- 'Oh, damn.'
- 'Damn!'
- Yeah!
- Too hot!
- Hi.
So there we go.
So why would she be mad at you?
There's no... Me?
Bunney,
what are you talking about?
(Jen)
No, I'm kidding. No, it's fine.
(all)
Cheers.
One more.
One more. One more.
(Heidi)
'Give me a lap dance, Jen,
for your birthday.'
Give me a lap dance.
[cheering]
It was a joke.
Alright! After party!
[instrumental music]
(Whitney)
'So I think that we're'
'setting up
for a meeting in here.'
How many are there?
Well, let's just
set 'em on first and then
we'll decide
how we're gonna space.
- Ahem.
- 'Did you go out last night?'
Yeah, went out to, um
Les Deux for Jen's birthday.
'Did you have fun?'
I was there, they
didn't stay the whole time.
They ended up leaving me,
I guess the four of them
went back to Brody's condo
last night.
- Oh, yeah?
- 'Jen called me...'
And she's like, "Hey,
I need to ask you something."
But I... A-And then I was like,
"What do you need to ask me?"
'She's like, "You know
what I need to ask you."'
I was like,
"Are you asking me if I care
if you hook up with Brody?"
And she was like, "Yeah."
- Oh! She said, "Yeah?"
- And I'm like--
She had the nerve
to ask you that
as if she shouldn't have
known in the first place?
And of course, Jen told me
that it was Spencer
the whole time being like,
"You should hook up with Brody."
You know,
'cause Spencer hates me.
Well, then, Jen should be
strong enough to be like
"Obviously, Lauren's
my first priority," and...
But it's like I know Heidi was
there too, and it's just like
I'm so tired of my friends
just screwing me over.
Yeah, people just need to get
their priorities straight.
You know, what I'm saying?
They're cool to hang out with,
but really, is it really worth
like screwing
a friend over for that guy?
I mean, obviously,
they have no idea
'what they're doing right now.'
Oh!
[instrumental music]
(Chiara)
'Wait, and did they
end up hooking up?'
Yeah, they hooked up.
And Heidi was there, she could
have stopped the situation.
Heidi should have stopped it.
She not just could,
she should have...
And Jen and Lauren
have been friends
since they were,
like, four or five.
So she shouldn't even
have went.
- She should know.
- Right.
Especially,
since Lauren seems so...nice.
She's so nice.
She's such a good friend.
She got Jen diamonds
for her birthday.
And Jen repaid her
by hanging out with a guy
that she's kinda seeing?
I would be so pissed at Heidi
especially for egging
something like that on.
Yeah, I think, it's...
Spencer's, like
brainwashing her a little bit.
Like, I don't know what...
First of all
Heidi would never do that,
if it was a year ago.
Like, she would be like,
no, don't do that
like, that's, Lauren
and him are hanging out--
It's weird that Heidi
doesn't seem to value
Lauren enough to like...
And Jen too,
Jen grew up with her.
It sucks, because those are
her two best friends.
It's like, those are her
best, best friends.
Is she okay?
- No. She's not okay.
- No.
It's really sad.
I feel bad for Lauren.
'I do too.'
[instrumental music]
(Lauren)
'I'm just so sick
of the situation.'
[cellphone ringing]
Jen.
You and Heidi both act like
you did nothing wrong.
You did a really cut-throat
thing, and so did Heidi.
So you guys need to stop,
like, putting it on each other
and stop making it seem like
I'm making drama.
And, you know what,
I would expect it from someone
I didn't know, but not,
like, my oldest friend.
But it's just kinda like code,
Jen, that you don't really...
You don't hook up with people
that your friends, like
hung out with, or dated.
'So Heidi was in the room
as he was doing this?'
No, Jen, if you're sorry, you
don't sit there and make excuse
after excuse, you say,
I did a really bad thing
and you apologize.
You-You sounded super-sorry,
seriously, Jen
don't be at my apartment,
when I get home.
Mm!
Okay, then,
I'm sorry that I called
like, that's not an apology.
I mean,
not that I think Spencer
is, like, the issue, I think--
- Spencer is the issue.
- Yeah. I mean--
'He was, he started the issue,
but her behavior is the issue.'
Yeah.
'I mean, I don't wanna say
this in a harsh way'
but, like,
it's really time to evaluate
the friendships that you have--
I know, but that sucks, when
it's, your two best friends.
It's-It's awful.
(Whitney)
'Oh, I think
she's calling you again.'
I don't care.
[sighs]
[instrumental music]
[door knob rattles]
- Hi.
- Hey.
Um, so I need to talk to you
about what happened last night.
I had nothing to do
with any of this, it's like
I'm sorry, if I left you
and that hurt your feelings--
Like, If things are going,
gonna continue the way
they're going right now
then that's not okay, I
don't wanna live here anymore.
I just don't get how
this is becoming all on me
when it's, like, Jen's the one
who's, like,
making out with Brody--
Ask Jen,
I told, I told Jen, I said
"Don't be at the apartment
when I get home."
I don't wanna talk to you, I'm
not talking to Jen right now.
I'm livid with Jen.
Okay?
I am really shocked
by Jen's behavior.
But the thing is, last night
was just kind of like
'the straw that broke
the camel's back.'
Like, it's not a secret,
you know that things
aren't fine with us,
like, I really don't feel like
you're the same friend to me
as you used to be. I don't.
That's just so unfair, because
I feel like you put this wall
because you put this wall up
about Spencer. It's like--
Oh, my God!
I'm trying to be a good friend.
I am too!
So what am I supposed to do?
It's so unfair that,
it's like I have to choose
and it's like,
I'm trying to be here and--
No, you're not choosing,
you're not.
You don't even have to choose.
But you've chosen.
- Don't keep saying that--
- 'You have. You've chosen.'
- You make that up.
- You know what, you know what--
I consider, I consider...
I feel like if it continues
to go the way it is, like
I'm not gonna be friends
with you anymore.
'Like, all we do is, like, fight
or pretend things are fine'
and just not talk about
problems, and that's not
how best friends
should be at all.
And I feel like if we just
continue, then it's not...
It's just gonna get worse.
So then what do we do
to fix it?
'Cause I wanna fix it,
I don't wanna just stop
being best friends with you,
it's, like, I love you.
Heidi, we don't have to stop
being best friends
but something has to change.
So what are we gonna change?
I'm gonna be able to talk
to you about Spencer?
It's like, you know,
Spencer has you freakin'
like, brainwashed,
it's so sick to see.
'It is, like,
yo-you've changed so much'
'since you've been
with Spencer, you have.'
I'm so tired of being like,
"Pay attention to me.
- Pay attention to me."
- That's not true.
You have to remind me
of certain things, people--
I don't have to remind you
to be my best friend.
I'm not reminding you to be
my best friend, but Lauren
you're putting me
in the weirdest position
'cause it's like, I'm trying
here, but I can't talk
to you about my boyfriend,
so what do you want me to do?
I thought you were making
an effort with Spencer too.
It's like, this is the whole
hardest thing.
- I am making an effort!
- I know!
I'm making an effort,
and then he does * * *
like he did last night,
he's a sucky person!
- He's a sucky person!
- Lauren.
I hate Spencer,
I'm never gonna like Spencer.
He did a really
messed up thing last night.
'I know that he pushed Jen
and Brody together.'
Why did he do it?
'Give me a good reason
why he did it.'
Did Brody tell you that
she kissed him?
- Yes.
- Bitch.
I haven't felt so betrayed
by best friends in so long.
- Like--
- I didn't do anything.
Yeah, exactly.
You didn't do anything!
I can't
control people, Lauren.
So you... You sit on the phone
and tell him you love him.
If he loved you,
he wouldn't do * * * like that
'to your best friend.'
You know that
it's not gonna be okay
until you
and Spencer are broken up.
Like, you know that.
Because he is the problem.
We don't have any problems
without him.
♪ And I wait ♪
♪ You never were the same ♪
♪ Something in you changed ♪
♪ That day ♪
♪ And I am ♪
♪ All alone again ♪♪