Are you guys completely
fine again? Are you...
I haven't even talked to you
in like two days about it.
[sighing]
I decided to give Spencer
another chance.
I see so many qualities
that Jason had in him
like, just these
little like, mind tricks
that he plays you
and it's so frustrating.
It's like, I'd think
that because you watched me
go through all that,
you wouldn't do it.
It's just, it's different.
It's not different.
He's not a good person.
I'm telling you that
'cause I'm your friend.
Well, I'm just gonna have fun
and see what happens.
You know, really,
I feel like I can't even
talk to you, you're
my best friend right now
because you're not
gonna listen to me.
And you're gonna get
mad at me and I hate
thinking,
"is she gonna get mad at me
if I tell her the truth about
this guy, is it worth it?"
It's like, who's to say
he can't change?
I hope he changes.
That would be ideal for me.
- I-I want you to be happy.
- Can't I give him that chance?
Well, is it gonna be this huge
elephant in the room?
Are we not gonna be able,
like, to be close?
- Are we not gonna be able to...
- We're still gonna be friends.
I just,
it's an understanding.
You know, that I think you
really shouldn't be with him.
I just, I don't wanna talk
about him anymore.
I don't wanna hear
about him and I just...
I don't, I'm never
gonna hang out with him, so...
You know, if
it's gonna come between us
and if you're gonna,
like, be mad at me
and not be able to be
around me, then it's like--
You know what?
I've put in my two cents
and you know how I feel
and I'm gonna be there for you
when he screws you over.
'Cause he will.
- Can we leave soon?
- Yeah, we'll leave right now.
♪ One look was all it took ♪
♪ And everything
was set my darling ♪
♪ One look was all it took ♪
♪ And you were in my head
my darling ♪
♪ I stood like an open book ♪
♪ Waiting to be read
my darlin' ♪
♪ One look was all it took ♪
♪ And you were in my head
my darling ♪
♪ Ah ah ah... ♪♪
[whistling]
- Hi.
- Hello, darling.
- Are those for me?
- Yes, they're for you.
[grunting]
Thank you.
- There you go, sweetheart.
- Oh!
- Aah.
- They're beautiful!
Yeah, look, it looks
like a rose garden.
I broke the piggy bank
for those
so you better appreciate them.
Really? Thank you.
- How are you?
- Little stressed.
This whole thing
with Lauren is really hard.
God, I wish I hadn't been
such a jerk
to start out with
and made your life easier.
- She loved you at first.
- I know.
It's like, I don't want
it to be awkward
when I come home,
you know what I mean.
I don't want it to be like,
"Hey, where are you going?"
And then I can't be like
"Oh, I'm going to Spencer's."
Like, I never wanna
go through with her again
what we went through
with Jason. It was so hard.
We were, like,
hardly friends, you know--
So, the exact same situation
reversed that's happening
right now?
You would never
treat me like Jason.
You know what I mean,
like, it's, it was different.
Does she know
how much I love you?
Nobody does.
I don't think
people get it, it's like
Heidi is my number one.
That's two,
but one here.
Alright, what can I do
to get Lauren to like me again?
I think you just have
to prove yourself.
- To Lauren?
- To everybody.
[both laughing]
I gotta prove myself
to everybody?
Good luck.
So, are we having
a slumber party?
Yes, we are.
♪ And my friends ♪
♪ Would say ♪
♪ You're right you're wrong ♪
♪ You're right ♪♪
- Lauren.
- 'Hi.'
Look, Spencer
got you some flowers.
That's really nice of him.
Is he gonna give them
to Audrina tomorrow?
- No, they're just for you.
- 'Wow.'
[clicking tongue]
I got a bunch of good turkey.
Yum.
[instrumental music]
♪ Disappointment ♪
♪ Overtakes me ♪
♪ Can I go on? ♪
♪ Will you let me? ♪
♪ I can't believe that ♪
♪ I have to tell you ♪
♪ I must go now we've been... ♪
Alright, my darling.
I am leaving.
- Staying away tonight.
- Oh, you're not staying here?
- 'No, I'm not staying here.'
- Goodnight.
- Goodnight. Love you.
- Love you.
♪ Still here ♪
♪ It used to feel right ♪
♪ It used to be good ♪
♪ You supported you... ♪
[cellphone beeping]
♪ When my heart was ♪
♪ And now it's broken... ♪♪
- Hello?
- 'Hi.'
(Audrina)
'Do you wanna come eat with me?
I have a bunch of food.'
'I can make lasagna
and salad or something.'
Sold.
[doorbell ringing]
- Hello! How are you?
- Hi.
- Good.
- Good to see you.
Me and my mom
cooked this today.
And all we have to do
is really, just warm it up.
Oh, well, that's easy.
So, has Heidi made her mind up
about, um, Spencer?
- Yeah, he gets another chance.
- Really?
- Oh, my God.
- I tried.
- I tried to tell her, but--
- So did I.
I told her the truth
about everything.
Tell me, like,
what did he say to you
'when he asked you to come
meet him for ice cream?'
I have a feeling he was just
trying to get back at her
by using me,
but it didn't happen.
I'm sorry, I just could never
see you with Spenc--
Oh, God! Me either.
- 'Are we eating at the table?'
- Yeah.
Look at us adults.
Oh, my God.
She comes in tonight.
First of all,
she went and told him
that I don't like him,
and I guess he was, like
really bothered by it
because he went out
and bought me
a dozen long-stem roses.
What?
I feel like Spencer's gonna be
putting ideas
in her head, like, oh--
That's what it already seem,
remember he told her
Oh, Audrina and Lauren
are just trying to
like, get you against me?
- 'Mm-hmm.'
- That's how it's gonna turn.
He's gonna hurt her,
like, she's already in
it seems like, over her head.
I know, she is, I'm just,
it's just so much easier
to get out before you're--
- Before you're in too deep.
- Mm-hm.
I just feel like
it's gonna be really bad.
[upbeat music]
Have you, um, resolved things
with Heidi?
She hasn't slept at our house,
and just like never home.
It's one thing to have
a boyfriend, it's another thing
to just abandon your whole life.
You know, what I'm saying.
I feel bad because I did put her
in that situation
where it was like,
she knows I don't like him.
'Even, she said,
she's like, "I feel like'
"we're not gonna
be fine until, like
as long as me and Spencer
are together."
And I was like,
"Well, that's your decision.
You're the one
who's changing your behavior."
- Yeah. Yeah.
- 'I'm not changing anything.'
Because I think that you'd
probably gotten to the point
where all you want
is just your best friend.
[upbeat music]
♪ I lit the last match ♪
♪ And saw the last burn... ♪♪
(Heidi)
I can be
the biggest nerd ever.
[chuckling]
You are the biggest nerd ever.
- Guess what?
- Guess what. What?
I have really fun plans
for us this weekend.
What are your plans for us
this weekend?
Um, come to the club
with me and Lauren tonight.
No, I don't wanna go
to the club anymore.
It really means a lot to me--
All the club does
is create conflict.
"Spencer was just talking
to a girl."
That's what Lauren's gonna say
to you if I go to a club.
- "I saw him in the bathroom."
- No, she's not.
She's just not gonna care.
Oh, really? She's gonna all
of a sudden not care about us?
She's one of my friends,
and I need to spend
a little more girl time.
Um, why don't you
go without me?
I really don't like the girl,
Heidi.
- Be nice, Spencer.
- She's not nice to me.
She's gonna try, I think.
You know, I told her
that I wanna spend
more time with her
too, and make sure
that I don't cut out
my friends in my life.
♪ I see you girl ♪
♪ Shake what you got ♪
♪ I'm never ever ♪
♪ Wanting you to stop ♪
♪ I see that thing... ♪♪
I love this dress on you.
- Your boobies look pretty.
- Thanks, baby. You look pretty.
'It's time to, like, grow up
and just be like you know what?'
It's like, I think there's just
been a lot of miscommunication--
(Audrina)
'Well, it's not
a miscommunication, but--'
(Heidi)
'I'm sick of fighting
with people.'
Let's have some fun.
[indistinct chatter]
- Heidi
Let's go
[instrumental music]
♪ I ♪
♪ I won't let you go this time ♪
♪ I won't let you go
this time ♪♪
[instrumental music]
[knocking on door]
[gasps]
Whoa!
- How are you?
- Good, how are you?
Good.
Have a seat, beautiful.
Aah!
So what is all this drama
going on right now?
Heidi went into this
and everyone told her from
beginning,
you know, what if you're
getting involved with Spencer
'"He's a cool guy,
he's a lot of fun'
but don't get into
something serious with him."
Why were people
saying this, like?
Because when
they're hooking up
he goes the next day
and takes Audrina
out to lunch and gives her
the same flowers
that he gave to Heidi
the night before.
'And he hits on every girl.'
It's like,
but listen, I'm s...
Of course,
it was a little bit wrong
but maybe Spencer
feels threatened by you
because you're going
to Heidi and sayin'
stay away from Spencer,
he's shady, he's shady.
(Lauren)
'...that wasn't Heidi's place
to go tell him that.'
I would never ever
choose a guy over a friend.
Heidi seems happy, that's
all you should care about.
I watched my best friend cry
because of what
your best friend did to her.
Listen, but listen, have you
ever thought that, like
"Maybe she really,
really likes Spencer?"
If I was not getting along
with my best friend
I wouldn't be happy.
[instrumental music]
(Spencer)
'So what's up, player?'
So Lauren came over earlier.
And she's all upset about Heidi
and her not being friends
and I felt bad,
because she almost cried.
She needs to stop worrying
about other people's lives.
- Like, I get it.
- I told her that.
You're best friends, you guys
are like sisters. Da, da, dah.
It's like, "Okay, you don't
like Spencer, that's fine.
Stop letting it come
between our friendship."
- 'She goes around--'
- She's upset with--
- It's like, get over it.
- 'I know.'
I asked her,
"Well, what did Spencer do?"
It is so, and she brought up the
Audrina thing with the rose--
Oh, I got Heidi a dozen roses
and I gave
them to Heidi, right?
'And then Heidi turned right
around and gave them to Lauren.'
So, Lauren thinks
I got her a dozen roses.
But it's like, "Yeah, right,
am I spending a dollar on you?"
[instrumental music]
[cellphone ringing]
Hello, my darling.
How are you?
Uh, I've been better,
like, when I'm with you
and not hearing about
your good friend Lauren.
Why? What happened?
Well, she said that she knows
that you're not happy anymore.
And Brody's like,
"Well, she's always happy
"with Spencer, so I guess
she's only not happy
when she's with you," whatever.
I'm like the happiest I've ever
been in my entire life.
'She's the only one
that doesn't know that'
'cause she's
too busy being negative
and, I don't know,
I'm, I'm really, like fed up.
'I don't see how you guys
can even live together anymore'
''cause I'm not allowed to be
in the same room as her'
'it's just like...'
(Heidi)
'I just feel like I've been put'
'in the worst
situation possible.'
You know and she's
my best friend and now
it's so weird
and it's just getting weirder.
And this,
the whole thing is just
'so, so, so incredibly
out of control.'
I just want everything
to be normal.
I just want it to be back
when everything was fine
with everyone.
♪ Catch your demons ♪
♪ Like butterflies ♪
♪ In a a giant netting ♪
♪ Full of eager eyes ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm a comet ♪
♪ Burnin' up the sky ♪
♪ And fading into dust ♪
♪ And fallin' fast ♪
♪ But it's alright ♪
♪ Yeah it's only your life ♪
♪ It's alright ♪
♪ And you never ♪
♪ Get it right ♪
♪ No never ♪
♪ On the first... ♪♪
Ooh!
Hey. How was school?
[exhales]
Long.
[sighs]
Did you have a conversation
with Brody today?
I did.
(Heidi)
'Do you think I'm unhappy?'
'Brody said that
you were saying that'
'like, "I'm unhappy
and you know me."'
No, he said, I think Heidi's
really happy right now
and I said that
I wouldn't be really happy
if I had, like, if I had
barely talked to my best friend
in a week and a half,
that's what I said to him.
I don't want it to be
like this with us.
I don't think it's fair.
Oh, it's not?
How is it not fair?
I feel like I have to choose
between you and Spencer.
(Lauren)
You don't have to choose...
[sighs]
...but you have chosen
for the last week and a half.
Lauren, don't even say
things like that.
It just sucks, Heidi, I was
the only one of your friends
who was gonna say
something to your face
and it sucks that I did,
and I really
regret it
and next time, I won't.
Don't walk away like that
and just say something
'like that,
it's not about that--'
I don't wanna fight
with you right now.
'I don't wanna fight
with you, period.'
You're my best friend.
I love you more than anything.
You don't think I, my life sucks
when it's not fine with you?
It's like you're one of the most
important people in my life
ever, in my world,
it's like, I care about you
and I love you
more than anything, it's like--
Really, Heidi,
because I really think
that you would have made time,
you keep saying
'like, oh, you don't
wanna choose but you have.'
I haven't chosen.
Don't make it like that.
'I haven't chosen.
It's not like that at all.'
'It's like, I would love
to spend time with you'
'but I don't want
it to be awkward time...'
I want it to be normal
Heidi Lauren time
and it's like, I feel
like it won't be that way
as long as Spencer's
in my life.
How? Why not?
I told you I won't...
- 'I don't know, it's like...'
- I won't talk about him.
I know, but I still feel
like there's this weird space
between us,
do you not feel like that?
Okay, Heidi,
how would you feel right now
if I was like, "I'm gonna
go hang out with Jason."
- I like him again?
- It's a whole different issue.
- 'No, no, it's not, it's not.'
- Oh, really?
You came to me,
and you said all these things
and you put on line,
you were like, "I hate him--"
Because I know what happened.
I'm saying that I went
to you, and I made a risk.
And I said,
this is all this stuff.
I know, it's gonna be awkward,
but I think
it's more worth it for me
to say these things to you.
'I really, like I hoped that
you wouldn't make me'
'regret it but you really did.'
The first thing you did was go
and tell Spencer,
"Oh, Lauren hates you
Lauren hates you,"
so it's awkward.
I didn't say, "Lauren
hates you, Lauren hates you..."
Why would he buy me flowers
if you didn't say anything?
Uh, those were my flowers,
I was just joking
like, here,
Spencer bought you flowers.
I thought it was funny.
I thought it was a joke,
like, look
he bought Audrina flowers,
he bought you flowers
like, I'm sorry.
I really, like, um, don't even
wanna talk to you right now.
No, Lauren, you can't just
shut yourself off like that.
It's like, I'm reaching out, I'm
trying to have a conversation...
[door slams]
♪ Someday ♪
♪ There's not much
you can change ♪
♪ And did you really think ♪
♪ You're right this time ♪
♪ With what you've done to me ♪
♪ We'll meet the end someday ♪
♪ No time to contemplate... ♪
Do you wanna talk about this?
- 'Cause I really am leaving.
- 'Heidi...'
'I just really don't wanna
talk to you right now.'
Alright.
♪ The end ♪
♪ Today ♪
♪ Today ♪♪
[instrumental music]