Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Dexter...
Who's the guy that
dropped you off this morning?
We didn't sleep together,
if that's what you're
getting at.
You are certainly allowed
to be a player.
You remember Cassie, right?
- Yeah, new neighbor. Hi.
- Hi.
I kind of need to leave.
Go. I'll take care of Jamie.
We'll be fine.
Maybe we could reschedule?
Yeah.
I'd like that.
Any reason why you haven't
taken the sergeant's exam?
I got your brother on my ass
about taking
the sergeant's test--
And what is so wrong
about trying to better yourself?
You nailed it, bro.
Is he your choice for sergeant?
I'm ready to take on
more responsibility.
I want you to strongly
consider making her sergeant.
I think you may be my father.
Family showing up like that
out of nowhere?
A lot of times,
they just want something.
I want to hire you to do
a background check on someone.
You really think
she's here to rip you off?
I don't know what to think.
Norma Rivera.
She'd been having an affair
with the boss, Ed Hamilton.
- Dad, what's going on?
- The Hamilton son.
Did you go to the place
where Norma Rivera was killed?
I did.
What did you see in your,
you know, analysis?
- Leave the kid alone.
- He killed her.
You don't know that.
Your only witness recanted.
No reason to make enemies
unless we really have to.
Where's Yates?
So this is finally over.
My tormenter's dead.
Thanks to you, Dexter.
And Deb.
I'm glad to see
that you two have managed
to find your way
back to each other.
Well, the family
that kills together...
A few days ago,
everything seemed hopeless
between Deb and me.
But through Dr. Vogel,
I've got my sister back.
It's beautiful out here,
Dexter.
I wanted to be with family.
Accidents happen,
shattering our sense
of control,
if not our lives.
It's no accident
that Zach Hamilton is here.
He's drawn to blood, like me.
Did he kill Norma Rivera?
After a week of vetting him,
I haven't been able
to find definitive proof.
But I'm sure,
if I keep following him,
the truth will become clear.
Or it could get murkier.
Dexter.
Have you taken on Zach Hamilton
as a patient?
It's nice to see you, too.
I have to protect you
from another murderer now?
How did he even get to you?
His father contacted me
because of my reputation
for working with psychopaths.
He's concerned
about his son's behavior,
his propensity for violence.
I think it's more
than a propensity.
I think Zach Hamilton
killed Norma Rivera.
And I take it that
you followed him here today
because you're planning
to kill him?
The thought had
crossed my mind, yes,
if I can find solid proof.
Well, then it would seem
that we have a conflict
of interest.
I don't believe this.
You're going to work
with another killer
after what happened with Yates?
Dexter,
I appreciate your concern,
but I'm not going to talk
about Zach Hamilton
with you any further.
It wouldn't be ethical.
Suddenly,
you're worried about ethics?
I know.
I threw them out the window
when I met you
because my life
was on the line.
Now the threat is over.
And you're bringing
another threat into your life.
It's my work.
What can I say?
I treat dangerous people.
It's a hazard of the job.
Besides, you have no proof
that Zach Hamilton
is guilty of anything.
I will.
If you do,
then come to see me first
before you do anything,
and we'll have
another conversation.
Would you do me that favor?
We'll see.
I mean, this is
why she tracked me down,
to hit me up for money.
You don't know that.
I mean, maybe she genuinely
wanted to get to know you.
Well, at the same time
her Hyundai's being repossessed?
Has she asked you for money?
No, but she always seems
to be missing her purse
when the check comes.
I thought we had
a real connection.
You like having Niki
in your life?
Yeah, I do.
Then why don't you
just wait it out
and see how it plays out?
In the meantime,
you can enjoy her company.
Okay.
Thanks, Deb.
Welcome.
Deb, got a new case.
Let me guess, someone suspects
their significant other
is fucking around on them.
Yeah...but this one
is a bit different.
How?
Because the person is me,
and the significant other,
my sister's ass-chasing,
shithead boyfriend.
Kevin Wyman, notorious player,
frequents a singles bar
in a hotel where he keeps
a hotel suite.
Have you tried
talking to her about this?
Susan doesn't listen to me.
It'd just push her
more quickly into his arms.
So that's off the table.
Well, going behind her back
seems kind of fucked up.
It's got to be done this way.
I gotta catch this guy
in the act.
I gotta present her
with the facts.
Okay, but you're doing it
by yourself.
I need your help on this, Deb.
It'd be a lot less conspicuous
if we work this as a couple.
Well, I'm not sure
if I'm comfortable.
Well, are you comfortable
getting a paycheck?
Okay, boss.
Thank you.
Where does this piece go?
Right here.
Very good.
Dex, don't forget,
my birthday picnic's
in a few days, okay?
On the beach,
outside of Papa's.
Bring Harrison.
- Yeah, we'll be there.
- Great.
You know who else
will be there?
Cassie.
I heard you have a date
with her today.
No, it's not a date.
I just felt like I owed her one
after we both bailed
on your dinner the other night.
Oh, my God,
why won't you just admit
that you like her and that
I am an awesome matchmaker?
I'll admit that
you're an awesome nanny.
You'll have to settle for that.
We'll revisit this
after the date.
Oh, by the way,
the TV remote has
been missing since yesterday.
I think somebody hid it,
but I can't get anything
out of him.
Harrison,
did you take the TV remote?
No.
- Do you know where it is?
- No.
He says he didn't take it.
Right.
Guess I'll just
keep looking for it.
Homicide in Liberty City.
All right, Harrison,
it looks like
you're going to have to finish
that puzzle on your own.
I'm doing all the work anyway.
Yeah, you are.
- Bye.
Welcome
to spatter-land.
Hope you brought extra string.
Never leave home without it.
Good news.
We have the victim's boyfriend
in custody.
A witness saw him
taking off from the scene,
and he forgot
to change his bloody socks.
God bless stupid killers.
Once again, drawn to blood.
Looks like Zach has just
given me the in I need.
Zach Hamilton, right?
You were at my house.
That's right.
You guys find out
who killed Norma?
No luck.
It's a dead end.
So you like
to shoot crime scenes?
Yeah, I got a police scanner
app on my phone.
It's better
than sitting at home,
playing video games.
You ever been on the other
side of the yellow tape?
Nope.
This is as close
as I've gotten.
Well, come on.
Are you serious?
Yeah,
just don't touch anything.
Whoa.
This is amazing.
I remember that feeling.
Awe, wonder.
It only fed the urge.
Hey, can I take some pictures?
It's usually against protocol,
but what the hell?
Go ahead.
Cool. Thanks.
So what happened to her?
She was stabbed.
Yeah, obviously.
But, like, you know, how?
If I open up to him,
maybe he'll open up to me.
Come on.
I can handle it.
Well, the victim
tried to defend herself.
There were defensive wounds
on her body,
but you can also tell
by these big, round drops
on the ground.
And this multiple
cast-off spatter
suggests that she was stabbed
several times.
And the arterial spurting here
indicates that the killer
severed her carotid artery
with the first stab.
You can tell all that
just by looking at the blood?
Pretty much.
Awesome.
So I heard you caught
the guy who did it.
- Yeah, her boyfriend.
- How?
He was sloppy.
Left a bloody print and DNA.
Plus, he was spotted
driving away from the scene.
Oh, yeah?
What kind of car?
He must have heard
his Porsche was seen
at Norma's apartment.
No one noticed.
So the killer,
he--
he should've worn gloves
and long sleeves,
made sure he was covered up.
He's making this
a teaching moment.
Well, yeah, if he was smart.
The kid's a quick study,
but that doesn't prove
he killed Norma Rivera.
Uh, so, hey,
I-I gotta get going,
but thanks.
Hey, why don't you
give me a call
when you print those up?
I'd love to take a look.
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess I could do that.
Time to make
another connection.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Thank you for doing this
with me.
When you own a food truck,
you kinda have to scope out
the competition constantly.
Plus I just really love to eat.
Yeah, no problem.
I wouldn't miss these
peanut butter and Nutella fries
- for anything.
- Mm-hmm.
So you're indulging me
in my favorite pastime.
What do you like to do for fun?
You know, normal stuff.
Like what?
Um...
I like spending time
with my son.
Mm, I already know
you're a great dad.
What else?
I love my job.
But that's work.
What are you passionate about?
I like to bowl.
You're passionate
about bowling?
No.
Of course not.
I, uh, just do it for fun,
once in a while.
Uh, what about your weekends
or your free time?
Oh, I have a boat.
Oh, I love to sail.
No, it's a motorboat.
Oh.
You water-ski?
No.
- Race?
- No.
Do you scuba dive?
No.
What do you do on your boat?
I just...
take it out and...
turn around and come back.
That's it?
That's all I can tell you.
I think we may need
some alcohol.
Right.
Dating is harder
than I remember.
Oh, this guy
is fucking pathetic.
I get that you hate the guy,
but looking isn't cheating.
It's a slow night.
Give him a minute.
So you said Susan
doesn't listen.
Does that mean you all
have a strained relationship?
Not from my end, no.
But from hers?
Yeah, you know, probably.
I mean, look, I couldn't wait
to get away from my old man,
and unfortunately,
Susan was just a kid.
You know, I should have
at least picked up the phone.
But I never did,
you know, so...
Well, you can't undo the past.
And families fuck you up.
That's just the way it is.
Well, I can stop Susan
from fucking up her future.
I can do that.
It looks like he's
packing it in for the night.
Elway, if you wanna
catch this guy cheating,
why don't I set him up
and see if he takes the bait?
No, I don't want you
doing that.
I worked Vice.
I've done worse
than that before.
I just need to get
a couple of pictures
of him hitting on you.
Certainly nothing more
than that.
Are you sure?
I mean, I could marry him,
maybe pop out
a couple of babies.
Let's go.
Dexter, thanks for coming.
Sure.
Couldn't wait to show you
these photos.
Yeah, no problem.
It's on my way to work.
Donut?
Fuckin' A.
Mmm.
Well?
He treats the blood
like a swimsuit model.
Well...
very colorful.
You know,
a lot of photographers
like to mute down their reds.
You know,
find it too distracting,
but I like to ride
the saturation.
Hmm.
You think I overdid it?
No way.
These are you.
That's the important thing.
Well, I can work you up
some prints, if you want.
I mean, I wouldn't have 'em
if it weren't for you.
Actually, I think I have
plenty of my own.
Right.
Of course.
I forget it was a crime scene.
Keep thinking that dead chick
spilled all that blood
just for me.
Who's she?
Uh, it's nothing.
Just a lens test.
New 300 millimeter.
Fucking monster.
Wow.
Excuse me.
Yep?
Jesus, are you still drunk
from last night
or are you starting
a new bender?
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, I said okay.
Uh, I gotta go.
- Anything wrong?
- No, it's fine.
I just gotta go.
Sure, some other time then.
I'll have to find another way
to get to him.
Ah, lieutenant.
Tell me something.
Did you decide
you don't need a sergeant?
Sir?
I expected to hear
an announcement by now.
What's going on?
To tell you the truth,
I'm having trouble
narrowing down my choice.
I know you want me
to pick Miller.
And on paper,
I can't argue with that.
She scored higher on the test,
she's got the experience,
the track record--
She's African-American,
a woman.
Here's the thing,
Quinn has his attributes too.
Name one.
He's street-smart.
Look, I know
what's going on here.
What do you mean?
You want me to be the bad guy.
You want me to insist that
you promote Miller over Quinn.
That way you can tell Quinn,
"Hey, sorry, I had no choice."
- I'm not sure that's--
- You're lieutenant now.
It's time to grow
a set of balls.
I want to hear something
by the end of the day.
Just like old times, huh?
You, me, steak, beer.
Yeah, it's been a while.
So how are things?
Good, great.
You?
Fine. Better.
Good. I'm glad.
Me too.
I think these are done.
So how's work?
Uh, crazy.
Elway wants to catch
his sister's boyfriend
fucking around on her,
so I offered myself as bait
so he'd get it done.
What--you did what?
I used to do it
all the time in Vice.
Yeah, and you hated it.
Why would you put yourself
in that position again?
Because he's my boss.
And 'cause I can only take
one control freak at a time.
Sorry.
This is tough.
A little.
Not exactly worth living for.
What?
You said that once,
when you tasted
one of my steaks,
that it was worth living for.
For some reason,
I've always remembered that.
It'll get easier, Dex.
We're just getting
back in the saddle, you know?
Yeah, I think we might
be eating a saddle.
Are you still
seeing Dr. Vogel?
Yeah, it's too bad for me
there's no magic pill
to cure PTSD.
Well, as long
as she's helping you.
I don't get it.
Like, she knows
every fucking thing
about our lives because of dad,
but I don't know
Jack shit about her.
Like, where'd she get
that fucking accent?
And who the fuck is rich?
- Her husband.
- She was married?
Yeah, when I first
looked into her,
I found out some stuff
about her background,
and she was married
to a Dr. Richard Vogel.
Oh.
Okay, so Harrison's asleep.
And look what I found
under his bed.
Ooh, someone's in trouble.
He lied about it.
At least now we know why.
I hope it's under warranty,
or I'll be stuck
with whatever's on PBS kids
for the foreseeable future.
I'll talk to him.
Okay.
Enjoy your dinner, guys.
Bye.
Should I be worried
that Harrison's lying?
He's four, doofus.
Right.
This steak tastes like asshole.
Yeah.
Let's order pizza.
With pineapple, please.
Not on my half.
Sorry, cow.
What's up?
I'm promoting Miller
to sergeant.
Say that again?
I'm giving Miller the job.
I'm sorry.
I just think she's
the most qualified candidate.
Are you fucking kidding me?
I mean, after all the quizzes,
and the speeches
about bettering my life?
You actually made me want this,
and now you're going
to take it away.
Why? 'Cause I didn't solve
the fucking Norma Rivera case?
No, of course not.
It's just a lot of other stuff
I can't ignore, man.
The Nadia thing,
shooting Novikov.
You know what?
Fuck it.
You did what you thought
was right.
Leave it at that.
Hey.
I need everything you got
on the Norma Rivera case,
anything that points
to Zach Hamilton.
Uh, forensically,
there's not much.
There's nothing, actually.
Fuck it.
I'll just tail
the little prick 24-7
until I get what I need.
If Quinn's stalking Zach,
how can I?
Won't even know I'm there
till I bust him.
You mind if I come along?
You want to come along?
Yeah, things
are kind of slow here.
I'm going a little stir crazy.
Maybe you could use
another set of eyes?
Sure.
I mean,
you think Miller's clean?
Come on.
You dig deep enough
on anyone in this department,
and you know what you find?
- What?
- The shit.
It's there.
I mean, we all got it.
I know you know
what I'm talking about.
Yeah, I can't argue with that.
We've all got the shit.
Yeah.
Big difference is,
some people get away
with theirs,
and some people don't.
Well, you're a good detective.
It'll work out.
Yeah, I'm just worried
about how Jamie's
going to take it.
I think she was all excited
about me moving up
in the world,
making something
out of my life.
She'll probably break up
with my ass now.
Jesus Christ, I mean,
how many pictures
of fucking women in tights
does this pervert need?
Apparently, a lot.
How's Deb doing?
I've been worried about her.
She's good.
She's much better.
You guys work out
whatever your issue was?
What do you mean?
Well, I mean, you guys
have been connected at the hip
for most of your lives.
All of a sudden,
you're not talking,
you don't see each other.
Somebody shit
in somebody's Cheerios.
Yeah.
Just typical
brother and sister stuff.
- It's no big deal.
- Hmm.
Something had her fucked up.
I mean, how weird was it
that she confessed
to killing LaGuerta?
I should have stayed
in my office.
What was that about?
That's the woman in the photo
that Zach
didn't want me to see.
And he isn't looking
at the class,
he's looking at her.
You know what I'm saying?
Fortunately, Quinn isn't.
People do weird stuff
when they've had
too much to drink and they're
under a lot of stress.
We may never know
what that was all about.
All right.
See you guys later, yeah?
- Looks like they're done.
- So is our guy.
Buckle up.
- Hey.
Wow.
Okay, uh--
- What?
- You look incredible.
Good job.
Well, that's the point.
Don't look
so fucking surprised.
Well, you didn't leave me
a lot of places
to put the transmitter.
Are you bitching?
'Cause I'm the one
helping you, remember?
I just don't want to touch
anything I'm not supposed to.
Here.
Thank you.
- Mic?
- There you go.
I'm not looking.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Yep.
- All right.
Quickly,
just say something for me.
You blush like a little girl.
Okay, just--
just get him alone.
That's all I need.
I'll take it from there, okay?
- Okay.
- Thank you.
I'm really glad we met.
Me too.
You know, I didn't know
if I mentioned it,
but tonight's kind of
a celebration.
- Yeah?
- Mm.
Closed a huge deal.
Two blocks downtown,
prime views of the bay.
It's going to rent
through the roof,
and I get a big piece of it.
Something tells me you like
getting a big piece
of everything.
Whenever I can manage.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Just wish
I had a present for you.
What do you say
we migrate to my suite?
Got a nice little private bar.
It's a lot quieter
than this place.
All done here.
You're going to love the views.
It's beautiful.
Nice, light music.
It'll be real nice.
No, save it for the room.
Oh, what, are you
playing hard to get?
I don't like to kiss in public.
- Ah, you're bashful.
- Mm-hmm, maybe.
Get your fucking hands
off of her!
Jesus, Elway.
The hell is going on?
She's wired, douchebag.
You're done.
You fucking son of a bitch.
You know what, you're going
to call Susan tonight.
You're going
to tell her it's over.
If you don't,
she's getting an email
with a video attachment.
You got it?
- Yeah, I got it.
- Good.
You're an asshole.
The fuck are you thinking?
I'm sorry, all right?
I-I-I just--
seeing him paw
all over you like that,
I don't like that shit.
I'm sorry about your top.
That's okay.
It's all right.
I got it.
Sofia Fuentes,
current place of employment,
the Cypress Harbor Yacht Club,
which is owned
by Zach's family.
That's where Zach must have
first laid eyes on her.
If Zach likes to take pictures
of his victims
before he's killed them,
chances are he likes
after photos as well.
If he did kill Norma Rivera,
then he's got the photos
to prove it.
Sofia.
Probably his next victim.
Now I just need to find
any photos of Norma Rivera.
Norma Rivera.
Taken seconds
after she was killed,
the pool of blood
around her head growing
from one image to the next.
Zach Hamilton,
murder weapon in hand.
All the proof I need.
You wanted proof.
There it is.
Zach Hamilton
killed Norma Rivera.
Yes.
I know.
- You know?
- Mm.
Zach told me
during our first session.
But you didn't tell me
because of your unflinching
sense of ethics?
Oh, forget ethics.
Why would I help
facilitate the death
of someone I see potential in?
Potential?
He's a killer.
He deserves to die.
Isn't that a little intolerant,
coming from you?
I don't kill innocent people.
But you might have,
if it hadn't been
for Harry and me.
You could even be
on death row right now, huh?
- Right.
- But you were spared.
Yeah, I was spared
because of the code.
That's an interesting idea.
What do you mean?
What if we were
to teach Zach the code?
- You can't be serious.
- Why not?
It never occurred to me
to try again,
because I didn't have Harry.
But now I have you.
Maybe it's time to see
if the experiment will work.
This isn't a science project.
No, but it's a matter
of life and death.
Zach's life is on the line.
What possibly makes you think
Zach could be taught the code?
I told you,
I see something in him.
And it worked with you.
Zach and I are nothing alike.
No, of course not.
You are definitely
one of a kind.
He killed an innocent,
and he's getting ready
to do it again.
He needs to die.
Harrison.
I never intended to have a son,
but now he's the one thing
in my life
that seems most right.
There she is!
Hi!
Yay.
Aww, mwah.
- Happy Birthday.
- Aw, thanks, Dex.
Thank you.
Can I go play?
Yeah, sure.
Have fun.
Stay close, Harrison.
Yeah, I'm, um--
I'm not sure if he's a date
or just a friend.
I mean, what I do know
is that she's very attractive
and men like her,
so if you want a chance,
you better move fast.
Right.
Uh, I think I'm going
to go grab a beer.
You know, this may sound weird,
and I don't mean
to sound creepy or anything,
but I think I really like you.
Aww.
I like you, too.
I'm not really ready
to call you "Dad,"
but, uh, you're cool.
"Cool"?
Usually, I'm the only one
that calls me that.
So that's awesome.
Oh, hey.
I got you something.
What?
It's really not a big deal.
It's not a big deal?
You're giving me $5,000?
- Hey...
- Why?
I know you could really use it.
But you should know
that that's really all
that I can afford.
I don't understand.
How do you know
that I could use it?
Well, you know,
I just did a little research
on you.
You checked into me?
Like a criminal?
No, I just wanted to make sure
you were who you said you were.
And that I wasn't after you
for your money?
- I just--
- Look, I have debts,
but they're soon to be paid,
and that's not really
any of your business.
I wouldn't ask you for this.
I'm really sorry.
Do you understand
that it was really hard
for me to do this?
To find my father?
But I felt like it was worth it
to get to know you.
You know, maybe I was wrong.
Here you go.
No, thank you.
- Hey, Niki--
- All right, everyone.
I'd like to make a toast.
To the best kid sister
a guy could ever have, Jamie.
Aww, thank you.
I love you.
Happy Birthday.
I love you, too.
Aww, thank you, guys.
Thank you so much for coming.
You guys are the best,
and it really is so nice
to have you all
here in one place together.
I love you guys.
Cheers.
Happy Birthday.
And here's to you,
Sergeant Quinn.
I know it's premature,
but I just wanted--
- Way premature.
- You didn't tell her?
I didn't want to upset her
on her birthday.
No.
You didn't get the job?
You didn't give it to him?
I had to go with the person
I thought would be
best for the job.
And how is that not Joey?
Hey, it's okay.
He gave the promotion
to Miller.
It's--you know.
But going for sergeant
was your idea
in the first place.
You set him up.
I didn't mean to--
Jesus, Angel.
- Hey.
- Dexter, hi.
How are you?
I'm great.
You?
Great.
Nice party, huh?
Yeah.
The beach.
Harrison looks like
he's having a really nice time.
Yep.
Uh, Dexter, this is Oliver.
Oliver, Dexter.
- Nice to meet you.
- Yeah, you too.
I didn't know if you wanted
the Belgian brown
or the oatmeal stout
or the German Pilsner,
so I just got you the one
with the moose on it.
Can't go wrong with a moose.
I'm going to go
check on Harrison.
Okay, take care.
- Is that okay?
- Yeah, that's great.
- That's your neighbor, right?
- Yes.
What happened with Susan?
Wyman break up with her?
Yeah.
Yeah, he did.
So it's a win.
Why do you look like someone
just ran over your dog?
I just got off the phone
with her,
and she couldn't stop crying.
She thinks it's all her fault,
like somehow, she's not
good enough or something.
Well, she would've caught
him cheating eventually.
The result
would have been the same.
Yeah, but it wouldn't be me
that made her cry.
Jesus, I just feel like shit.
People can't help
sticking their noses in
when it's someone
they care about.
I know.
You tried to tell me.
So does that mean
you care about me?
Only to the extent
that you sign my paycheck.
Touche.
Okay, what are we
going to read tonight?
Let me guess.
"Wee Monkeys."
Before I read to you,
I gotta talk to you
about the TV remote.
You said you didn't take it,
but Jamie found it
under your bed.
I didn't mean to break it.
I was pretending
it was a thunder blaster,
and I dropped it
in the kitchen.
Well, yeah, that's okay.
Accidents happen.
But you lied to me.
That's a big deal.
We should never lie.
But, daddy,
you lie.
What do you mean?
You told me doggy got lost.
I saw you
throw him in the trash.
I had to rescue him.
You're right.
I lied.
Doggy got dirty, and I tried
to clean him up,
and when I couldn't,
I threw him away.
I'm sorry I lied to you,
Harrison.
That's okay.
But can I keep him?
I really love him.
He's soaked in blood
that links me to a murder.
Yeah, but maybe he should live
under the bed.
- Okay.
"Wee Monkeys."
"Wee Monkeys"!
It's no accident,
Harrison catching me in a lie.
I can live with my lies,
but how long can Harrison
before he finally sees through?
I should be back
in a few hours.
Sorry to keep you late
on your birthday.
Trust me, it'll probably be
the highlight of my day.
Vogel doesn't want me
to kill Zach,
but she's wrong about him.
He deserves nothing
but my table.
He's here.
Hey, Zach, it's Dexter.
Where is he?
Why would Zach
buy a car for $1,200?
Because the one mistake he made
with Norma Rivera
was showing up to kill her
in a red Porsche.
He's going
to kill Sofia tonight.
Cypress Harbor Yacht Club.
Yes, hi, could you tell me
if Sofia Fuentes
is working tonight?
She gets off here
in a few minutes.
Thank you.
Zach, waiting to make his move.
And Quinn, still trying
to prove he's a good cop.
- He Dex.
- Hey.
Look, this is probably
none of my business,
but I feel like I should
tell you about Quinn.
Okay.
He thinks you're going
to break up with him.
Break up with him?
Why?
'Cause he didn't make sergeant.
That's crazy.
Why would he think that?
Maybe you should, um,
invite him over.
I think he's feeling
pretty down.
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
Thanks, Dex, for calling.
That really is so sweet of you.
Sure.
Quinn problem solved.
And there's Sofia.
Zach's father.
Sofia is Hamilton's mistress,
just like Norma before her.
What is he doing?
Hey.
I know what you're doing.
Quinn.
You playing detective?
Watching Zach?
Yeah, you caught me.
I'm going to see Jamie.
Keep an eye on Zach.
Jesus.
What the fuck?
What are you doing?
Why were you going
to kill your father?
What are you talking about?
I wasn't trying
to kill my--
I know you killed
Norma Rivera.
I thought you were going
to kill Sofia.
But you were going
after your father.
- Why?
- You're crazy.
I didn't try
and kill my father.
You tell me one more lie,
and I'll kill you.
- I had to.
- Why?
Because he's killing my mother.
She's drinking herself to death
because of him.
Over the years,
one affair after another,
and he doesn't even
try and hide it.
I-I thought killing Norma
would put an end to it,
but two days later,
he's banging some hostess
from the club.
I knew if I wanted it to stop,
I had to kill dad.
So that's what this
is all about,
you trying to protect
your mother?
You actually care about her?
Of course I do.
She's my mother.
But showing up
at crime scenes, accidents,
taking pictures
of all the blood,
this is about more than
just your mother, isn't it?
No, I had to protect her.
Yeah, I believe you.
But you killed
because you want to kill.
- No.
- Yes.
To take a living person
and make them dead,
imagining that you
can actually hear the moment
when their heart stops beating,
smell the blood
as it pools across the floor.
I can't help it.
It just builds up inside me,
all these years.
But Norma was the first time
I ever followed through.
And how was it,
once you'd killed her?
It--it felt like
this huge weight
was lifted off my chest,
this release of something
horrible inside me.
Like you were finally
in control.
Yes.
You should just go ahead
and kill me.
Why?
'Cause if you don't,
I know I'll do it again.
I don't want to be like this,
but I can't help it.
I just am.
I'm some kind of freak.
A monster.
Yes.
You haven't told anyone else
about this, have you?
Besides Dr. Vogel.
No, I couldn't.
You never had a Harry.
A what?
Someone to talk to.
Someone to teach you.
Some things happen to us
by accident.
Others are choices.
There are parts of me
that I can never share
with my own son.
But with Zach--
could I teach him?
Am I ready for this,
to be a spiritual father?
So how'd your sting go
with Elway?
Terribly.
Didn't work out?
No, it worked out fine,
but--
What?
He likes me.
Oh.
That's a bad thing?
Well, he likes me
'cause he doesn't know
a fucking thing about me.
"Yeah, I killed two people,
"and tried to kill myself
and my brother.
But sorry, what kind of wine
would you like to order?"
I mean, what the fuck?
Yeah, I kind of know
what you mean.
How are things with Cassie?
Um, yeah, I don't think
there's much of a future there.
Maybe the Morgans just
aren't meant for relationships.
Yeah, maybe not.
But hey, life is good.
You know,
I'm feeling optimistic
for the first time in a while.
I'm even thinking
about taking on
a kind of...intern.
Hmm.
Well, that's a big step
for you, right?
Letting some novice
into your private lab.
Yeah.
Hey, are you okay?
I don't feel so good.
What's wrong?
I feel kind of dizzy.
Deb?
Hello, Dexter.
Remember me?
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com