Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Dexter...
I've come to believe
that the killer could be
one of my former patients.
He sent both packages to you.
Maybe he doesn't know
how to find me.
- Yet.
- Well, I need to get to him
before he gets to me.
- I've got my eye on Joey Quinn.
- Quinn?
There's no way he can pass
that sergeant exam.
He'll pass.
I stuck my neck out
on the line for you.
You'd better not fuck this up.
Lieutenant Morgan?
- Is there a problem, officer?
- Well, yes.
You're in a car, drunk,
with an open container.
- Quinn.
- Why did she call you?
She's a friend.
I couldn't say no.
I mean, come on,
you used to fuck her.
There is nothing going on
between me and Deb.
I want to know if there
was anything unusual
about my father's death.
He killed himself, Dexter.
Harry walked in
on what he created,
and he couldn't live
with himself.
Trust me when I say that
there's a place in this world
for your son.
I told you, you're perfect.
How can you still say that
when you know
what I've done to Deb?
I shot the wrong person
in that trailer.
Your sister just confessed
to killing LaGuerta.
What?
I'm telling
the whole fucking truth!
There's nothing you can do
to stop me!
- Deb, please.
- Stop--!
I thought I could fix this,
but you're right--I can't.
I just keep making her worse.
Do you really think
you can help her?
Yes.
Stop!
Do it, Debra.
Shoot him.
This is not who you are.
You are a good cop.
You're a good person.
You're not like him.
Put him down!
It's true.
Everything she said.
You're a good person.
It's okay.
Do what you gotta do.
Dex...
Tell me what you saw.
I don't want to talk about it.
Debra, I brought you here
so we can begin to strip away
the power this place
holds over you.
Talking about it's
not gonna change anything.
Neither is continuing
to repress what happened here.
I'm not repressing shit.
And I sure as shit
don't need you to remind me
about what happened here.
You know, Dexter's
need to kill was born
in a container
much like this one,
and he's been trapped side
its walls ever since.
As a psychopath, he will
never be able to break free.
But you can,
by reliving the events
of that night over and over--
I killed him.
I shot Dexter
instead of LaGuerta.
That's what I saw.
Now, unless you're gonna
fucking handcuff me again,
I'd really like to go.
When you shot Dexter,
how did that make you feel?
Better. Worse.
I don't fuckin' know.
What does--what does it
even matter?
I mean, LaGuerta is still dead.
- What else could you have done?
- Arrested him.
Splendid, now your brother
is on death row. Go on.
- We could have run.
- Only to eventually be caught.
You go to jail, Dexter gets
the death penalty again.
Debra, you've become so obsessed
with the life you've taken,
you've forgotten
the life you saved.
Of course you're
fucking defending him.
You fucking created him.
You're using him to track
a serial killer.
This isn't about Dexter or me.
This is about
you getting better.
Maybe I don't fucking
want to get better.
I don't believe that.
Why the fuck
should I even trust you?
Why the motherfuck
do you even care?
Are you upset?
Yes, I am.
Good.
At least you're no longer
avoiding your feelings.
We're done for now.
For today.
There are countless ways
to inflict
physical trauma
on the human body,
and sometimes
the deadliest wounds
are the ones we barely see.
They run deep,
like the ones
I've inflicted on Deb.
What are we looking at?
Well, most of the blows
are to her face.
There's some bruising
around the neck.
It doesn't look like
there was much of a struggle.
No signs of a break-in.
Yeah, given the lack
of defensive wounds
and the close proximity
of her attacker,
I'd say you're looking
for someone she knew
- we have a name?
- Norma Rivera.
Landlord said she lived here
by herself.
Just got off the phone
with the vic's employer.
She was a housekeeper
in Biscayne Bay.
- Nice zip code.
- Yeah, um...
they all said she had an ex
in and out of her life,
Roberto Sagastume.
Me and Miller can swing by
his place.
He had a record.
It's good to see you
taking the initiative,
like any good sergeant should.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Yo...
You got my test back?
You nailed it, bro.
Now wipe that stupid grin off
your face before Miller sees it.
Yeah--no, I've just
never been this happy
to get back a positive test,
you know?
What does my sister see in you?
Half-pint.
Before I forget,
there was this little hottie
asking for you
back at the station earlier.
And you seem surprised, why?
Said she'd come by later.
They always come back for more.
Hey.
Any word on Deb?
Yeah, Dr. Vogel says
she's still day-to-day.
Let her know
I was thinking about her.
I will.
She's gonna be okay.
Opening shop.
A run.
Caffeine.
All morning routines.
But lately, mine consists
of coming here,
waiting for the woman
I left my sister with
to do what I couldn't--
make Deb whole again.
- Thank you.
- How is she?
Well, you still remain
the focal point
of your sister's pain.
- I want to see her.
- No, I think it's better
you continue to keep
your distance for now.
It's been almost a week.
Dexter, I am still not sure
if your sister
has hit rock bottom yet.
What is it?
I just want you to prepare
for the possibility
that Debra may never be able
to have you back in her life.
No.
I won't...
just let her go.
So, have you had better luck
with our killer?
I crossed off three more
former patients from your book.
Who's next on the list?
- Chapter seven.
- A.J. Yates.
I'll check back in
once I check him out.
A.J. Yates.
According to Vogel's book,
he attacked a classmate
with a chair at 12.
Institutionalized at 15.
Seems Vogel tried to channel
his violent tendencies,
but he was beyond her help.
Eventually, he was transferred
to another hospital.
Now Yates seems to be
a productive member of society.
He's a bundler--
cable, phone, Internet.
But I need to know if murder
is part of the package.
There's nothing here.
Nothing in Vogel's notes
about brain surgery.
His scar.
Is that the mark of one
of her "unconventional methods"?
Thanks for letting me
use the treadmill.
Better you than me.
I'm not much
for running in place.
Is that your shrink way
of saying that I have been?
Is it?
Care for some tea?
How about something stronger?
Come on, I just ran four Miles.
What's one beer?
The drinks and the drugs
were keeping you numb,
making the symptoms
of your PTSD worse.
Ass off the table.
How long are you expecting me
to stay here?
I see a lot of your father
in you.
Harry wrestled with the same
doubts regarding Dexter.
You're not as alone
as you might think.
Honestly, I don't see
what the problem is.
He had everything laid out
on his bedroom floor.
Dexter saw in the paper
how this guy got off
on a technicality,
so he was stalking him,
vetting him.
Even found a kill room
in an abandoned house
near the park.
Just how we taught him.
What did you tell Dexter?
That this guy
was too high-profile.
That he'd be missed,
and that Dexter
would have to wait.
He went along with
my decision...for now.
Is this ever gonna be right?
What we've done?
I mean,
Dexter isn't a kid anymore.
He's becoming a man.
He's gonna kill.
We knew that day was coming.
But what happens when
I finally tell him it's okay?
What happens when he finally
knows what it's like
to take another person's life?
The code will do
what it was designed to do--
allow Dexter to be
who he was meant to be.
But what if it doesn't?
What if the code
doesn't keep him in check?
What then?
What if this has all been
some horrible mistake?
Obviously, Harry
came around when he realized,
what else could he have done?
Locked Dexter away
in an institution?
Or do nothing until he took
an innocent life?
Or protect your brother,
giving him the tools
that he would need
to channel his urges.
The same way you protected
Dexter in that container.
It's not the same.
You're wrong.
- Deb.
- I can't just accept it.
I'm not like him.
I'm not like you.
Dexter--Dex--
Dexter is fucking Dexter.
Debra...
Harry did not make a mistake
saving Dexter's life,
and neither did you.
That night in the container,
Dexter was being exactly
who he was meant to be,
and so were you--
a loving sister.
- I--
- Will get through this.
- Can I keep that tape?
- Yes.
He had everything laid out
on his bedroom floor.
Dexter saw in the paper
how this guy
got off on a technicality--
Dexter, you shouldn't be here.
I was vetting Yates.
- What did you do to him?
- What are you going on about?
He has a scar on his head
exactly where your killer
has been harvesting
brain fragments.
Is he another one
of your little experiments?
We can talk about this,
but not here.
Not with Debra
in the other room.
An X-ray revealed a lesion
on Yates's brain.
I suspected it was contributing
to his violent behavior,
so I...
I suggested the new hospital
remove it.
I never knew whether
they even performed the surgery.
When I do what I do,
I have to know everything.
Sorry for the oversight.
Now, why don't you tell me
the real reason you're here?
You could have just called
for the scar.
Is it regarding what I said
about letting your sister go?
Dexter, I assure you
that I'm not judging
your relationship with Debra.
I'm just trying to manage
your expectations.
Why, because she thinks
I'm a monster?
You think I don't know
that I'm the one responsible
for the pain she's in?
That's why she's here with you.
You have to get her
to forgive me.
Whatever it takes,
you have to find a way.
I need her in my life.
- You need her?
- Yes.
I understand that you love
Debra, in your own way.
"In my own way."
But why do you think
you need her?
I just do.
Deb looks up to you.
Isn't that what you said?
She used to.
And that made you feel good
about yourself?
Yes.
Well, no wonder
you feel so lost.
Debra became a mirror,
reflecting a positive image
of yourself
that you used to balance out
with the notion of yourself
as a monster.
Now that mirror is cracked,
and the only reflection you see
is one of darkness.
You make it sound like
that part of me isn't real.
You are no monster.
You never have been.
Anyone on my table
would disagree.
Dexter, a monster,
by definition,
is outside of nature,
but you're a part of
the natural order of things,
with purpose, and value.
A right to exist.
And when you come
to accept that,
you'll no longer be dependent
on Debra, or anyone's,
validation.
I'll still want her in my life.
Want, but not need.
No van.
No Yates.
No one home.
"Monterey Nursing Home."
"Dad's 76th birthday."
It seems Yates found a way
to keep his family in his life.
Will I be able
to do the same with Deb?
Vogel says I don't need her.
But if that's true,
will I be able to let her go
if that's what she needs?
Women's shoes.
- Hello?
- It's me.
I'm at Yates's house.
- Have you found something?
- Women's shoes.
Individual shoes, not pairs,
some of them older.
High heels are a far cry
from brains.
It's not exactly
your killer's usual M.O.
If you recall
when all this began,
I expressed my doubts
that this was the work
of someone new to killing.
Albert wouldn't be the first
to alter his methods.
Yeah, still, something
about it doesn't quite add up.
But, just to be safe,
I'm pulling prints
off the shoes.
I'll run them through
the station's database
for missing persons
and homicide victims,
but they're only partials.
I won't expect anything back
until the morning.
And I have my son tonight.
Understood.
I'll let you know what I find.
Vogel.
She found herself a hero.
Hi.
Hello.
You must be Dexter.
I'm Cassie, 4-B.
And you're
in my kitchen because?
I'm a friend of Jamie's and
I ran out of laundry detergent.
Daddy!
I see you two have met.
I hope you don't mind.
Oh, who am I to deny
a neighbor clean clothes.
So, dinner's in the oven.
I'll see you in the morning?
- Sure.
- I'll walk you out.
- Mwah.
- Nice to meet you, Dexter.
You too.
Bye!
She's nice.
But does she have
a kissy-neck?
- I knew you would pass!
- I didn't.
Oh, thank you for that.
This one used to have
to write the combination
of his station locker
on his wrist
for a month
when he first got here.
So what?
My memory sucks.
All you needed
was the right encouragement.
I don't even want to know
what that means.
We're empty.
You know, I really am
so proud of you.
I couldn't have done it
without you.
You wouldn't believe
who was behind the wheel--
Debra Morgan, the former
Lieutenant of Homicide,
passed out, piss drunk.
Come on, Joey--
Joey, just let it go.
Man, I don't really know
who was fucked up more,
her or the parking meter
she ran over.
Hey.
How about a little
professional discretion?
Yeah, well, I believe
that we're off the clock.
No, I know, but you could
lower your voice, you know?
Yeah, sure.
No problem.
Thanks.
- Who's that guy?
- I don't know.
I think he used to bone her
or something.
Probably the way Morgan
made lieutenant--on her back.
- Fuck!
- Hey, hey, hey!
That's enough!
Enough, I said!
Enough!
What the hell happened?
Someone was defending
his ex-girlfriend's honor.
Get him out of here.
- You know what? It's fine.
- I'm sorry.
Let's just go.
Hey, how about a round
on the house?
- All right, lieutenant.
- Fuck.
So...we're good?
Mm.
- Ow, babe--babe, my ribs.
- Yeah?
Oh.
I'm so sorry.
Ow!
- How many, mister?
- Two.
One for me, and one for Dan.
Two it is.
Sorry I'm late.
Who's Dan?
Pet elephant.
You don't see him?
You want some pancakes, Dan?
Eat up.
Make sure Dan doesn't
get any syrup on the couch.
Okay.
My car died.
That "check engine" light
I kept ignoring?
Apparently,
it means what it says.
How did you get here?
Angel.
But, don't worry.
My car will only be in the shop
for a few days.
I'm gonna see if Cassie
can give us
a lift to Harrison's preschool.
You know, you made quite
an impression on her last night.
Impression?
She's single.
Just sayin'.
Hey, why don't you
take the SUV?
It's safer.
I'll clear my stuff out.
If you can drop me off
at the station,
I'll pick up a car
from the motor pool.
Sure you don't mind?
I don't if Dan doesn't.
How did I let you talk me
into this again?
I believe your price
was one beer.
- So, now what?
- You tell me.
Isn't this where you think
you belong?
No.
Frankly, I'm quite amazed
that you think you ever left.
Are we really gonna do this?
Debra, you shut yourself
inside these walls
for the last six months,
doing your damnedest
to shut everything
and everyone out.
So, why don't we?
What the fuck are you doing?
I want you to convince me
how killing Dexter
instead of LaGuerta
would be a better choice.
Open the fucking door.
LaGuerta.
She was on her knees,
where those blood stains are,
isn't that right?
She was your coworker,
your friend.
Why didn't you just stay
at the party
and let Dexter take care
of everything?
I had to stop him.
But Dexter can't help
what he is.
He has no conscience,
unlike you.
You knew the moment
you pointed that gun
at LaGuerta it was wrong,
and still,
you pulled the trigger.
You shot a woman in cold blood.
You let her bleed out
and did nothing.
You shot an innocent woman
for simply doing her job.
Because of Dexter.
And that's what
terrifies you the most.
You so desperately
want to believe that
if you had just shot Dexter,
then you wouldn't
have to face the hard truth
that if you had to do it
all over again,
you'd still choose him.
Because in your heart,
you know you will always
choose Dexter.
How do I make it right?
By finally accepting
that you're a good person
who was forced to do
a terrible thing.
And that you made the best
of an impossible situation.
You can walk out that door.
You can move forward.
The choice is yours.
It always has been.
Oh, lieutenant.
- A word?
- Of course.
I was just reviewing
the sergeant's exam results,
and it seems you were right
and I was wrong about Quinn.
Apparently, he can count
past his fingers and toes.
He was in the 85th percentile.
So was Miller.
In the 88th percentile,
to be exact.
I want you to strongly consider
making her sergeant.
Angie is good.
I like her, a lot.
But I'm still thinking Quinn's
the smarter choice--
All I said was
"Strongly consider."
This is your first departmental
promotion as lieutenant,
and it will reflect
on your command.
That being said,
it's your decision
and yours alone.
Three hits off the partials,
all reported missing.
Janet Thorton,
taken two weeks ago.
Looks like Yates
killed these women,
but I still can't be sure
he's the one after Vogel.
Not until he's on my table
and we have
a little talk first.
Where are we on Norma Rivera?
- We're trying to find--
- Miller.
Address for the ex-boyfriend
is no good.
So far, nobody's seen him.
Got back the M.E.'s report.
They found semen.
I'm testing it to see if it's
a match for the ex-boyfriend.
Would explain
why he's off the grid.
She invites him over--
Things get heated,
he kills her, panics,
and goes on the run.
That's one theory, anyway.
Okay, let's find this guy.
- We're on it.
- "Dex'bose."
Favor--I need you to stay away
from the lab for a bit.
That little hottie
who's been looking for me
is coming up the elevator,
and we might need
a little alone time.
No problem.
Yeah, you would know
all about that.
You're better than that.
Come on, here.
There's a 20 in it for anyone
who directs her to my lab
and is cool about it.
- Done.
- Okay.
I'm on my own.
Perfect.
Angel.
I get it, okay?
You're pissed about last night.
I had to run a tab
so that asshole patrolman
wouldn't press charges.
Do you realize that if Matthews
would have caught wind
of this, he would've had
all the ammo he needed
to shoot down this promotion?
I'm sorry.
I lost my cool.
Well, I need my sergeant
to be able to keep his.
A bar fight?
Technically, your place
is a restaurant.
Come on, it's not like
you haven't done the same.
I mean, you put a guy
in the fucking hospital
for running his mouth about
how LaGuerta was using hers.
Allegedly.
And the difference is,
I wasn't up for promotion.
I had already made sergeant.
You want to fix this?
Solve this case.
Excuse me?
Are you Vincent Masuka?
The one, the only.
But, you can call me Vince...
just as long as you call.
Okay.
I'm Niki.
I'm a student
at "U" of "M."
Oh, yeah.
My Alma Mater.
Come in.
You must be majoring
in...beautiful.
- This is really hard.
- I know the feeling.
I think you may be my father.
You were a sperm donor
in college, right?
Mm-hmm.
But you have curls.
Yeah, my mom.
Holy...
Oh, fuck.
This was a bad idea.
Sorry.
Okay, that's embarrassing.
It's okay.
No, don't worry.
It's okay, don't--
don't--don't--don't--
it's okay.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, my God.
You've got my soulful
yet haunting eyes.
Night, Marty.
See you tomorrow.
We do have filing cabinets,
you know.
This is kind of my process.
What are you even doing here?
I thought you
were taking time off.
Turns out, time off
isn't all it's cracked up to be.
I just wanted
to get a head start
on some of the cases
that you left for me.
Well, we're gonna need food.
- "We"?
- Yeah, we.
You look like you could use
a hand, and I'm starving.
You know, when I need a break,
I've got maybe two days
at the most.
And then I go crazy.
I end up right back here.
What about you?
What makes you crazy?
- Family shit.
- Mm.
Nothing says family
like love...
and shit.
Unfortunately, my father
was an expert in the latter.
- Texas oil.
- Texas oil?
Mm.
Fuck, I hope I'm holding
my plastic fork correctly.
Exactly.
He was all rules, all the time.
My moving to Miami to be a cop,
that was about
the biggest "fuck you"
I could think of at the time.
I'm sure you understand
my dismay
when I got out of the academy
and I realized
it was nothing but rules.
Everybody there was probably
just like your father.
You know what
the worst part was?
I knew I had made
a huge fucking mistake,
but there was no way in hell
I was gonna give him
the smug pleasure
of knowing he was right.
So I waited until he died,
quit the force,
and opened up this place.
Looks like you're doing
pretty well for yourself.
Trust me,
I'm still the black sheep.
The look on my mother's face
every time she goes
into the country club,
has to explain
to one of her friends
that her son is a P.I.?
That's gotta be pretty close
to priceless.
Mm.
My dad was everything to me.
I loved him.
And while he's not the man
I thought he was...
Well, I'm--
I'm realizing we're
more alike than I thought.
To dead dads.
Long may they haunt us.
It's a better toast
if you open it.
I'm good.
Vogel says I'm not a monster...
but that's exactly
the part of me
she's expecting to remove Yates
as a threat.
A threat that seems
to have left in a hurry
and taken all his shoes.
Does this prove Yates
is who I'm looking for?
The only way
to know for sure is...
find where he's hiding.
He saw me here,
heard everything.
Bone saw.
Specimen jars.
His own cut-by-numbers guide.
Yates is the brain surgeon.
Vogel needs to know.
I know her.
I pulled her print.
Yates must have stabbed her,
nicked her left
pulmonary artery,
left her for dead,
unaware cramming her
inside that cart
would put pressure on the wound
and stop it from bleeding.
Now I have to do the same.
It'll hold, but not for long.
Do you think the girl
will be all right?
She lost a lot of blood,
but I stemmed the bleeding
and I dropped her off
in front of the E.R.
I got back here
as fast as I could.
Oh, God, has he been
doing all this because of me?
We can't know
until we find him.
Let's hope there's something
on here that'll tell me how...
These are patient files.
Your patient files.
That's not possible.
This last one's
dated just two weeks ago.
Dexter, don't.
What is this?
You were keeping notes on me?
It's a journal.
I've always had a journal.
You were writing down
everything we did,
everything we talked about.
It's all in here.
I never used your name.
Yates, nor anyone else
for that matter,
could possibly know
who you are.
"Somehow, he's deluded himself
"into thinking his feelings
for his sister are genuine,
unaware there are no
real emotions behind them."
Dexter, I--
I never meant--
What am I, a subject
for another one of your books?
Is that what these are for?
Answer the question!
My notes...
it's how I process--
You were experimenting
on me with Harry,
and you still are.
I'm nothing but a lab rat,
just like Yates.
That's not true.
You know that.
Is that why you want
to keep me apart from Deb?
You know, just another way
to isolate your subject,
see what he'll do?
- Dexter--
- Don't.
When Yates is dead,
you are out of my life.
It's over.
You understand?
Or do you need
to write it down?
I understand.
I walked into the room, and--
- Go on, tell me.
- The blood.
Evelyn, there was
so much blood, on plastic.
Dexter had placed it everywhere.
The walls, the ceiling.
There was a table
in the middle of the room.
- A table with--
- The body?
Parts of one.
And when Dexter turned,
the look on his face--
he--he was so proud.
When--the man Dexter killed,
he was a drug dealer.
He murdered your partner.
He was going to get away
with it.
But he was a person.
Who, according to the code,
deserved--
No one deserves
to be in pieces...
in bags.
The code is a theory, an idea.
But what I saw--
what Dexter did--
what we did!
I don't think I can live
with this.
Fuck, and I'm supposed to?
- Hello?
- Mr. Yates?
Yeah, that's me.
I'm afraid
we have some bad news.
Your father's heart is failing.
How bad is it?
We think
you should come quickly.
He might not have much time.
Dad.
I got here as fast as I could.
I'm right here.
Can you hear me?
It was you?
I was counting on you
being the good son.
They'll be here any second.
Room 26, code blue!
We're losing him.
We're losing him!
To save his own life,
Yates was willing
to take his father's.
Vogel believes I'm just like
all her other experiments--
a psychopath who can't
form real connections.
But she's wrong.
Deb isn't a prop, like Yates's
father was to his son.
She's more than a mirror.
She's family.
If I have a purpose, and value,
and a right to exist,
so do my feelings for Deb.
This experiment is over.
Vogel can go to hell.
Jamie packing you
a lunch these days?
It's for you.
I just came back
from Good Samaritan.
I need you to run the blood
on the clothes
of a stabbing victim,
Janet Thorton.
- She still alive?
- Still in surgery.
And the son of a bitch
who stabbed her
broke all of her toes.
- How soon do you need this?
- Very.
On my way back to the hospital
now to get a statement
as soon as the docs say
she's out of the woods.
Let me know what comes back
on those clothes.
Will do.
Deb.
What the fuck?
- Hey.
You here to see Dex?
- Yeah.
- Hmm.
Everything okay?
'Cause last time I saw you--
Yeah, I am sorry about that.
I'm so sorry I put you
in that position.
I'm sorry I got so mad at you
for calling Dex.
No, it's okay.
I mean, you asked me not to.
I was in a really bad place,
but, uh--you know, you were
just looking out for me,
like you always do.
Things are so easy with you.
I wish it was like that
with Jamie.
I just keep getting
tripped up, you know?
You all all right?
Eh, she's jealous.
She thinks there's
still something between us.
Make it work with Jamie.
I want you happy.
You mean so much to me, Joey.
Don't you fucking forget that.
Thanks.
You sure you're okay?
I gotta go.
Good-bye, Joey.
Deb.
The body forms scar tissue
to close a wound.
Has my sister
begun to do the same?
Eventually, scars fade.
Who knows?
With enough time,
you may not even remember
how you got them.
Dex.
Hey, Deb.
What's up?
We should talk.
It's important.
Yates can wait.
My sister can't.
Sure, I'd like that.
Just, not here.
Can we take a ride?
It's good to see you.
Vogel said it was best
I stay away.
What the fuck does she know?
If it's any comfort,
we're not on the best
of terms anymore.
She doesn't understand us,
Dexter.
Exactly.
She said I might lose you...
but we'll always
be together, right?
Vogel had these DVDs
of her and dad.
Did she ever show them to you?
A couple.
You?
There was one
that was really interesting.
It was, um...
just before dad died.
It was his last session
with her.
Did dad kill himself?
Yeah.
A few years back,
Matthews told me the truth.
Harry OD'd on his
heart medication.
Was it because of you?
He thought
he had created a monster.
I think I know how he felt...
why he killed himself.
But he only got it half right.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com