Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Dexter...
- Dex...
- Shoot him.
Do what you gotta do.
Oh, my God!
Whoever Deb was
before killing LaGuerta,
that person is dead.
Oh, my God!
What we think is the shooter
approached the vehicle
from behind.
El Sapo drew his gun.
I know you killed El Sapo.
What if I weren't here
to cover your ass?
You really want
to play the 'what if' game?
What's going on with Debra?
It's between me and her.
It's affecting you.
We're not going
to talk about Deb.
Here I thought
we were gonna make it
to one minute
before you mentioned
your old fiancee.
I-I got your brother
on my ass
about taking
the sergeant's test.
You're on my ass about Deb.
Interior insular cortex
is missing,
just like the last one.
So we have a serial.
Vogel was right.
Lyle Sussman.
I don't know anybody
by that name.
It doesn't mean
he doesn't know you.
He was coerced.
Sussman was never
a real killer.
He's just another victim.
You were wrong about me.
I destroyed Deb.
I'm a mistake.
You're exactly
what you need to be.
Daddy?
Harrison?
My tummy hurts.
Harrison, did you eat
a whole box of popsicles?
Harrison?
Why?
Because I love them.
All right.
Come on.
Drink this.
It'll make you feel better.
I promise.
Good boy.
A tiny shot of pink
is all it takes
to fix my son's pain.
I just wish it were that easy
to help Deb.
Um...
What?
Lieutenant Morgan?
Formerly known as.
Have you been drinking?
- There a problem, officer?
- Well, yes.
You're in a car, drunk,
with an open container.
Several, actually.
Well, at least I pulled over.
I've had a really bad
couple of days.
Maybe you could just
cut me some slack?
- I wish I could, but--
- But what?
There's been damage
to city property.
Property damage?
Are you fucking kidding me?
I'm gonna need you
to get out of the car, please.
Oh, mother shit.
Is there someone
I can call for you?
Your brother, maybe?
No, fucking don't call Dexter.
Quinn.
Yeah.
I'll be right there.
Is everything okay?
Um, yeah.
Just cop stuff.
- Okay.
- I'll call you later.
Okay.
Deb.
I'm up.
You okay?
I feel like
I got hit by a truck.
Jesus, Deb.
Oh, God, please,
just save me the lecture, okay?
My head hurts
like a motherfucker.
I'm not gonna lecture you.
They book you yet?
No, not yet.
They kept me out
of the drunk tank, though.
Thank God
for professional courtesy.
All right.
Let me see
if I can get you out of this.
Hey.
How you doing?
Can I get a little help?
What can I do for you?
Deb's had me
on such a roller coaster,
I actually appreciate
walking into familiar territory.
Lyle Sussman's cabin.
But where's the body?
Dex?
This is our guy, Sussman.
The brain surgeon.
Not exactly.
Did the real brain surgeon
restage the crime scene,
obscuring any evidence
that Sussman's body
was ever hanging from a hook
in the back of his skull?
Give me a hand?
His front teeth are broken.
Looks like Sussman
put this shotgun in his mouth,
and blam,
blew his head off.
Or someone put the gun
in his mouth,
and pulled the trigger
post-mortem.
G.S.R. on Sussman's hands.
Maybe this asshole
finally found his conscience,
couldn't live with what he did.
No note, though.
Ah, suicide.
Makes our lives so much easier.
You should put that
on a t-shirt.
Whoever's after Vogel
wants the cops off the case.
Is Vogel here yet?
I just called her.
Where the fuck is Quinn?
You, uh, can thank me later.
You still keep
a stash of gum in here?
I can smell my own breath.
Hey, you sure you want
to go straight to work
after spending the night
in the station?
I mean, I could take you home.
You could shower.
I keep deodorant in my desk.
Thanks for the ride.
Deb, wait.
What?
Should I be worried?
About what?
About you.
Think you might have a problem?
You mean
like a drinking problem?
I'm just saying.
Are you serious?
You, of all people,
are accusing me
of having a drinking problem?
I'm not accusing you
of anything.
How many times have you
shown up at a crime scene
in last night's clothes
smelling like booze?
A lot, okay?
Which means I've been
down this road,
so I get it.
I'm not down any fucking road.
But at least
when I was spinning out,
I had a reason.
What do you mean,
you had a reason?
You dumbass.
You turned down my proposal.
That was my reason.
So what's yours?
Maybe I just
don't know my own limits,
or something.
I didn't--
That's my boss.
I gotta go.
Deb--
You might want
to straighten up.
We have a new client
coming in at 9:00.
I'm frightened, Dexter.
He's escalating,
and we're left
to play catch up.
I'll run some tests
back at the lab,
but I'm guessing this tissue
belongs to Sussman.
Explains why the killer blew
his head off with a shotgun,
so nobody'd notice
the pieces were missing.
What part of the brain is it?
It's the occipital lobe.
It's responsible for vision.
He's sending us a message.
He's watching us.
That, and the "His" and "Hers"
boxes--
he's aware of me now,
not just you.
I'm sorry, Dexter,
to have dragged you into this.
He sent both packages to you.
Maybe he doesn't know
how to find me.
He probably doesn't even
know my name.
- Yet.
- Yeah, I know.
I need to get to him
before he gets to me.
I've been going
through your book,
and cross-referencing it
with the source files
and list of suspects.
Any progress?
I've managed to clear
the first two names.
So who's next?
- Ron Galuzzo.
- Mm.
According to your files,
he strangled his best friend
in high school,
but convinced you
that it was a bully?
Yeah.
It's rare that someone
can fool me like that.
At his hearing,
I argued for leniency,
but when I eventually got him
to admit that he'd been lying,
I reversed my recommendation.
So if Galuzzo read your book
and recognized
his story--
He would have realized
that he'd been institutionalized
until he was 21 because of me.
That's a pretty good reason
to hold a grudge.
- Dex.
- Excuse me.
It's about your sister.
What about her?
She got brought in
for a D.U.I. last night.
Shit.
I managed to get her out of it,
but still, it was pretty bad.
She asked me
not to say anything,
so I feel like kind of
a shit friend for telling you,
but I'm worried about her.
What the fuck's going on?
She's been having a hard time.
Yeah, I know.
But, man, this is, like,
a whole new level.
What are we gonna do?
I'll figure something out.
Thanks for the heads up.
I'm putting you up
for sergeant,
and you show up late?
Are you trying to make me
look like an asshole?
Sorry.
I had a situation.
You want a situation?
Come to the cabin.
What is it?
It's Deb.
She was brought in
for a D.U.I.
I need to check on her.
Is alcohol an issue for her?
I'm an issue for her.
She's acting this way
because of me.
But you can't keep taking on
your sister's problems,
especially right now.
It's my fault, okay?
Deb found out what I am.
She knows everything.
Everything?
How?
It's a long story.
Just suffice to say,
she's not handling it well.
You do really feel badly,
don't you?
Are you analyzing me now?
Well, it's just so unusual.
It's really not a good time.
Most of the time when
people think their partner's
having an affair,
their partner's
having an affair.
But not always, right?
No, certainly not always.
This is for you.
My assistant will explain
the retainer
and the payment schedule,
and we will get back to you
as soon as we've
found something.
So nervous.
Is that normal, to be nervous?
Well, people go through
a wide range of emotions.
I think the important thing is
finding out the truth.
Don't look at me.
I think the truth is overrated.
Call us
if you have any questions,
and we'll be in touch.
Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Well, it looks like
we have to work
on our client relation skills.
Are we done?
I need a fucking nap.
No, we're not done.
I've got something for you.
What is that?
A fucking shit shake?
Special custom-made
supplement formula.
It's got vitamins,
some electrolytes,
a couple Chinese herbs.
Gonna knock the hangover
right out of you.
How do you know I'm hung over?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
It's your brother.
Awesome.
Fucking awesome.
What do you want?
I heard about
what happened last night.
Fucking Quinn.
He's worried about you.
We both are.
You almost got a D.U.I.?
I think the operative word
is "almost."
It's not a big deal.
It's a very big deal.
This is why I didn't
want to tell you,
because I knew you'd freak out.
I'm not freaking out.
I'm just trying to help.
Fuck, Dexter.
I don't have time
for this, you know?
I have to find out
if some rich asshole
is banging some chick,
which he probably is,
so that I can tell her,
and she can
get a killer divorce settlement,
and they can move on
with their stupid,
fucking boring lives,
and I can move on with mine.
Because this is my life now.
Well, it wasn't always.
How about dinner tonight?
We can talk.
I don't want to talk to you.
Well, I'm gonna keep
showing up here until you do.
If I agree to dinner,
will you leave?
Yes.
Fine.
Great.
I'll pick you up at 8:00.
M.E.'s report is back
from the cabin.
They've officially ruled
Lyle Sussman's death
as a suicide.
So with that,
the brain surgeon case
is officially closed.
Okay.
I'll call Evelyn,
thank her for her help.
Evelyn?
Someone's got a high hard one
for the good doctor.
What did I say
about standing so close?
Any progress
on that El Sapo shooting?
Still no leads.
I've been going back and forth
with Fort Lauderdale P.D.
Apparently, El Sapo
was a suspect in the stabbing
of a smash and grab lowlife
by the name of Andrew Briggs.
The cops will never find out
that Deb killed El Sapo.
So right now,
I can focus on protecting Vogel,
and myself.
Ron Galuzzo.
He could be hunting me
right now.
Or he could be selling
fitness equipment at the mall.
Good work today, everyone.
Deputy Chief, you got a sec?
I just wanted to let you know
that I've been thinking
about what you said,
finding a new sergeant.
And I've got my eye
on Joey Quinn.
Quinn?
No way.
He's not sergeant material.
He's a good cop.
He's irresponsible,
unpredictable,
not to mention unintelligible.
There's no way he can pass
that sergeant exam.
He'll pass.
If you say so.
- Are you getting all this?
- Yeah.
This guy's making this
way too easy for us.
Yeah, it's really
fucking classy.
So tell me,
who's the guy that
dropped you off this morning?
Who?
Quinn?
He's a friend.
The kind of friend
that drops you off
in last night's clothes, huh?
God, we're not
sleeping together,
if that's what you're implying.
Not that it's any
of your fucking business.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
No judgment, no judgment,
no judgment.
You are certainly allowed
to be a player,
if you so choose.
What makes you think
I'm a player?
First, there's Briggs,
then there's, uh,
your new friend.
Well, he's not a new friend.
We used to date,
just not anymore.
Really?
So what happened?
He proposed.
I said no.
Jesus Christ.
He's certainly a better man
than I am.
Woman turns down my proposal,
I'm pretty fucking sure
I'm not gonna
stay friends with her.
Yeah, but that's just
because you're a giant pussy.
Yes.
Could be.
Ron Galuzzo.
If he is a killer,
then a mall
is the perfect watering hole
for him to choose his prey.
So, um, any of our products
is gonna make you
stay in the shape that you are.
Uh-huh.
And, uh, I need
to do some more work,
so I'll see you
a little bit later, okay?
It was dark at Sussman's cabin.
Does he recognize me?
You've got a keen eye,
my friend.
The Chiseler 300.
Top of the line.
Or is he just trying
to make a sale?
Just looking
for an all-over workout,
maximize my time.
Mind if I take
a body measurement?
Uh, sure.
Looks like you're already
in pretty good shape.
Oh, you have a very low
fat to muscle ratio.
Well, thanks.
I do what I can, you know.
Yeah, this equipment is more
for beginners,
people who don't already
have an established routine.
Mm.
Does he know who I am?
Is he trying to get rid of me?
I'm just looking
to change up my workout.
I'd love any suggestions.
That baby--
cut you up faster
than a chef at Benihana.
Come on, give it a try.
Okay.
He doesn't seem
to recognize me.
Whoa.
Careful, there.
Maybe a grudge against Vogel
will be harder to hide.
I like to read when I work out.
Keeps me
from getting motion sickness.
This one, I can't put down.
You heard of it?
I'm not much of a reader.
You've probably heard
of the author, though.
She's pretty famous.
They call her
"The Psychopath Whisperer."
Dr. Evelyn Vogel?
No, I've never heard of her.
Of course he's heard of Vogel.
She treated him.
He's lying.
You know, a fit guy like you,
you need to get
up to at least level five
to feel the full effect.
But why lie,
unless he has something to hide?
Yeah, I feel it.
- Yeah?
- Oh, yeah.
Don't forget to breathe.
You went to see Galuzzo?
You could have exposed us both.
It was worth the risk.
He's definitely
hiding something.
So now what?
I break into his house
tomorrow, when he's at work,
try to find hard evidence
that he's our man.
And in the meantime,
what if he comes for me?
Do you have any way
to protect yourself?
A gun.
I haven't used it for years.
Keep it loaded,
and call me if you need me.
I'm meeting Deb for dinner.
I'll check in with you later.
Uh, wait.
Just--
there's one thing
I was wondering about
since we last spoke.
Yes?
When Harry and I
came up with the code,
he insisted
that you only kill bad people.
And I insisted that
the first rule of the code be
don't get caught,
giving you a little
wiggle room.
Okay.
So my question is this.
When your sister found out
about who you were
and what you were doing,
why didn't you kill her?
What?
Not that I'd ever advocate
such a thing,
but since Debra knew
the truth about you,
she's clearly a risk--
I would never kill Debra.
She's my sister.
I love her.
What, exactly, do you love
about her?
Wha--what do you mean?
When a psychopath speaks
about love,
it doesn't really
mean the same thing
as for typical people.
So what do you love about her?
I-I don't know.
I love having steaks
and beer with her,
and until recently,
the fact that
she is always there for me,
the way she looked up to me.
But none of that
is really about Debra.
It's about what she does
for you.
So you're saying I'm selfish?
I'm not criticizing.
Selfless love is hard enough
for typical people.
And for psychopaths,
it's impossible.
So why are you telling me this?
So I'll feel bad about myself?
Quite the contrary.
I want you to revel
in what you are.
I told you, you're perfect.
How can you still say that
when you know
what I've done to Deb?
That's my point.
You're perfect as a psychopath.
All this talk
about helping Debra,
and loving her--
it's like you're Michelangelo
trying to play the banjo.
I'm trying
to be a good brother.
Why don't you
let me help Debra?
Because she wouldn't even
listen to you.
I'm the only one
who understands her.
Dexter, you admitted
to being the cause of her pain.
How can you expect
to be the solution?
I can handle Deb.
I've been doing it
my entire life.
All right, next question.
Physically evasive movements
to defeat
an officer's attempt
to control is
"A," active aggression,
"B," physical resistance,
"C," active resistance,
"D," active evasion?
"B," active aggression.
Okay, active aggression
is actually "A".
And, "B", it's wrong.
The answer is
"C," active resistance.
Wait, I'm confused.
Of course you are.
Matthews was right.
You're a fucking lost cause.
Jesus, Angel.
Easy.
Yeah, Angel.
I stuck my neck out
on the line for you
with Matthews.
You better not fuck this up.
Will you please
cut him some slack?
He's still tired
from being called out
in the middle of the night
on that case.
What case?
There's no case.
I'm, uh--
I'm gonna let you guys talk.
So where did you really go
at 4:00 A.M.?
Deb was in trouble
and needed my help.
She's been going through
kind of a hard time.
And why did she call you?
Why not her brother?
I don't think they're
getting along, you know,
and she's a friend.
I couldn't say no.
She's more than a friend.
I mean, come on,
you used to fuck her.
And now she's calling you
for everything.
What am I supposed to think?
Jamie, I swear to you,
there is nothing going on
between me and Deb.
Then why lie about it?
Because I didn't think
you'd understand.
Well, you're right.
I don't.
Enjoy your dinner.
The fuck are we doing
in this hellhole?
Can I get you something
to drink?
We have a wide array
of signature cocktails.
Yeah, I'll take
a Bourbon, neat.
Thank you.
Uh, two cokes, please.
I knew this was a mistake.
I wanted to show you something.
You see that man over there?
The father?
Yeah.
Does he look familiar?
Fuck if I know.
Fuck.
He's wearing Kevlar.
Don't fucking move!
So what, Dex?
That was a long time ago.
Yeah, but look.
See this guy,
the guy you saved?
That's him.
Right there.
His little girl
wouldn't have a father
if it weren't for you.
That's why I brought you
to this hellhole,
to show you that.
I know you think
you're a bad person, Deb,
after everything
that's happened,
but you're not.
You're a good person.
You brought a lot of good
to the world.
I'm fucking starving.
Have a nice day at the mall.
I realize that this is not
the outcome you were hoping for,
but it can help with
a favorable divorce settlement.
If you want,
we can forward those
to your attorney.
I don't know.
You don't have to decide now.
I realize
it's a lot to take in.
I mean, I don't know
if that's him.
I'm sorry?
This man in the pictures,
I'm not sure that's my husband.
That's him, all right.
Look, you can see his face.
Not clearly.
I mean, the lighting
isn't very good.
Mrs. Gerard, I assure you.
We're always very careful--
This was a mistake.
Mrs. Gerard--
I'm sorry
that I wasted your time.
I'll leave a check
at the front desk.
Is she fucking kidding?
That's obviously her husband.
She just didn't want to see it.
People get used
to living in denial.
It's just easier, you know?
Galuzzo has to be
the guy we're looking for.
Why would Galuzzo be such a slob
everywhere else but here?
That's why the kitchen
is so clean.
It's a kill room.
Galuzzo wasn't checking
my body fat
for my own fitness.
He was checking to see
if I was fit
to have as a main course.
He's definitely a butcher.
But does that
make him the brain surgeon?
Our killer leaves bodies out,
but Galuzzo keeps his bodies
to season and savor.
This brain
is completely intact,
marinating in some sort
of garlic sauce.
Galuzzo wouldn't waste brains
by sending them to Vogel.
They're a delicacy.
He eats them.
Which means whoever's after us
is still out there,
and he still has
the upper hand.
Fuck.
He's wearing Kevlar.
Deb, what are you doing here?
I want to make
an official statement.
How much have you had to drink?
One or two.
Why don't we get some coffee?
I don't want coffee.
I want to confess.
You want to confess to what?
I killed LaGuerta.
You what?
- I killed LaGuer--
- Shh.
Whoa, whoa.
Why don't we go someplace quiet
where we can talk?
Fuck!
I got you.
Take it easy.
Calm down.
Deb, what are you
talking about?
I told you.
I killed LaGuerta.
That doesn't make any sense.
It does.
On New Year's Eve,
I was at Papa's.
I called dispatch to find out
where she was going.
They said she was going
to the shipping yard,
where she met Estrada before.
Right, so you feel guilty
that you didn't back her up.
I don't feel guilty.
I am guilty.
No, you can't let yourself
think that way.
You had no way of knowing
what she was doing there.
I did know.
I killed her.
Deb, Estrada killed LaGuerta.
We both know that.
That's not what happened.
I'll tell you what happened.
I know what happened.
The bullet that killed LaGuerta
came from Estrada's gun.
He shot first.
It was a through and through.
That bullet
was never recovered.
She shot back.
He went down.
He got one more shot off,
and that bullet was traced
to Estrada's gun.
They both died
at the same time.
That's not true.
It is.
Remember, Dexter walked us
through it.
Dexter!
Oh, fuck.
Hey.
Oh, God, Joey,
you have to believe--
Okay, okay, okay.
I believe you.
All right?
Okay.
Here, just write down
everything you remember
from that night, all right?
- Okay.
- All right.
Good. Good.
Okay.
I'll be right back with you.
What about Arnold Gordon?
Trauma surgeon.
He definitely has
the right skill set.
Motive?
He always resented the fact
that I called him a psychopath,
and he threatened to hurt me
if ever I told anyone
that he was.
Morgan.
You need to get down
to the station.
I'm a little busy.
Yeah, well, your sister just
confessed to killing LaGuerta.
What?
She's drunk, high, fuck
and I don't know why.
I put her into the interrogation room
so no one else could see her.
Make sure she stays there.
I'm on my way.
All right.
Is everything okay?
It's Debra.
I need you to come
to the station with me.
Has something happened?
Yes.
I can't believe
she actually confessed.
I really thought I got her
to see that she's a good person.
This could have been
the only way
she could relieve herself
of the guilt.
I need you to help me
get her out of this.
Give your expert opinion
that she's having a breakdown
or something.
Are you sure?
This could be
the best thing for her.
Spending the rest
of her life in prison?
That's the last thing
Deb needs.
Or the last thing you need.
If Debra goes away,
odds are, you'll join her.
Admit it, Dexter.
You're mostly worried
about yourself.
That's not true.
I told you, I love her.
Not the same way she loves you.
When Debra killed LaGuerta,
it was real, selfless love.
She sacrificed everything
she believed in for you.
Can you see that?
Your sister
needs professional help.
There's nothing more
you can do.
Well, I can't just
give up on her.
I can't.
Dex, hey.
Dr. Vogel.
Mm-hmm.
She's an old friend
of Deb's and dad,
so I figured she could help.
Is she still
in the interrogation room?
Yeah.
Have you told anyone else
what she said?
Of course not.
It's crazy, right?
I mean, she's obviously
going through something.
She's likely suffering from
posttraumatic stress disorder,
after Captain LaGuerta's death.
She wasn't even there.
One of the most common
components of that
is survivor's guilt,
the belief that she could have
somehow prevented
what happened.
That's what I was telling her.
Not an uncommon response
in this situation.
We have to get her out of here.
What the fuck
are you doing here?
Watch the hallway.
Deb, this is Dr. Vogel.
She was a friend of dad's.
You can trust her.
She can help.
Hello, Debra.
I don't give a fuck
who you are.
Get the fuck out.
Debra, I know how much pain
you must be feeling.
But we need to talk
about this together
before you do something
that you might regret
for the rest of your life.
Regret?
The thing that I regret
happened six months ago.
I'm confessing everything.
I'm telling
the whole fucking truth!
There's nothing you can do
to stop me!
Deb, please, let us--
Quinn, let me--
That was interesting.
Here.
Hold this.
She passed out.
We must take her home to rest.
Let's get her out of here.
Is she gonna be okay?
Absolutely.
There may be some work to do,
but I promise,
Debra's gonna get through this.
Is there anything else
you need?
Not right now.
Thanks for calling.
You did the right thing.
What the fuck?
Are you sure she's gonna
be all right,
with everything she has
in her system?
Physically, she's fine.
It was a very low dose.
But emotionally...
this is all my fault.
Go easy on yourself.
I should have listened to you.
I thought I could fix this,
but you're right.
I can't.
I don't want to just keep
making her worse.
Do you really think
you can help her?
Yes.
Okay.
Go now.
Let me do what I do.
Wait.
Dexter, what are you doing?
She's gonna be pissed
when she wakes up,
maybe even violent.
I can handle her.
You don't know my sister.
Thanks.
Vogel was right.
I am perfect.
But only at one thing.
You're disgusting.
A cannibal.
A consumer of human flesh.
There was a time
when I couldn't imagine
anyone being what you are,
and doing what you do.
But now I realize
I'm just like you.
I consume everyone I love.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com