Sync and correction by Mlmlte
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Dexter...
It's no accident
that Zach Hamilton is here.
He's drawn to blood, like me.
And the arterial spurting here
indicates that the killer severed
the carotid artery
with the first stab.
I'm promoting Miller to Sergeant.
Are you fucking kidding me?
You actually made me want this,
and now you're gonna take it away.
I just did a little research on you.
You checked into me...
like a criminal.
Hey, Niki...
Dexter, this is Oliver.
- Oliver, Dexter.
- Nice to meet you.
Yeah, you too.
Zach Hamilton killed Norma Rivera.
He deserves to die.
Isn't that a little intolerant
coming from you?
What if you were
to teach Zach the code?
Maybe it's time to see
if the experiment will work.
What possibly makes you think
Zach could be taught the code?
I see something in him.
Why were you going
to kill your father?
Because he's killing my mother.
She's drinking herself to death
because of him.
You killed because you want to kill.
You should just go ahead and kill me.
Why?
'Cause if you don't,
then I will do it again.
I can't help it.
Am I ready to be a spiritual father?
Hey, are you okay?
- I don't feel so good.
- Deb?
Hello, Dexter.
Remember me?
Hello?
Dexter?
I was just about to leave you
another message.
Where have you been all morning?
The last thing I remember is...
Hannah.
Is everything all right?
Not if Hannah got to Deb.
I can't really talk now.
I just thought you should know
that Zach Hamilton called.
I'm so glad you decided
not to kill him, Dexter.
I have to go.
Deb, are you okay?
Dex, where the fuck are you?
Just a sec.
I'm outside of Kendall.
Are you alone?
Why wouldn't I be?
Why are you
on the other side of town?
I need you to come pick me up.
Are you okay to drive?
I think so.
I mean, who the fuck knows?
I woke up on the floor
feeling like shit.
You were gone.
What the...
What the fuck is happening?
Just come pick me up.
I'll text you the location.
We'll talk when you get here.
Hannah drugged us,
left me stranded
in the middle of nowhere.
If she's come back because she
wants one or both of us dead,
then why are we both still here?
It was Hannah, wasn't it?
It was.
I saw her before I blacked out,
but then I woke up here.
She must have drugged our food.
If Hannah poisoned us,
why didn't she kill us?
Who the fuck knows, Dexter?
Maybe we were supposed to eat more.
Or maybe she just wants
to let us know she's out there.
Maybe this was just the beginning.
If we were normal people, Dexter,
we would go
to the U.S. Marshal Service.
We can't do that.
She knows everything about me.
Yeah, but she didn't talk about you
the last time she was arrested.
Because she was in love with me.
Drugging me and leaving me
on the side of the road
might suggest that's changed.
So what the fuck
are we supposed to do?
There are
traffic surveillance cameras.
She had to have passed them.
I'll put in a request
for the footage,
get a license plate.
I thought this part
of my life was over.
So did I.
The moment I asked you to kill her
was the moment that I started
to lose myself,
and I'm just starting to get back.
I don't want to deal with this.
I want her gone.
Deb, I'll take care of this.
I promise.
Hannah... just thinking about her
throws me off course.
I have to put in a request
for the traffic footage.
Zach, what are you doing here?
You were supposed to meet me
at 10:00 this morning.
I've been waiting all day.
- You could have been followed.
- By who?
Oh, Detective Quinn?
No, he's pretty easy to lose.
But one day, he'll be there
when you don't expect him.
Don't ever come to my home again.
- I just wanted to talk to you...
- Ever.
We can't be seen in public together.
Do you understand?
That's your first lesson.
Okay. Jesus.
I'm... I'm sorry.
It's just...
I-I spoke to Dr. Vogel, and she...
What exactly did she tell you?
That you have this, like,
way of living that...
A-allows you to do what...
what you and I have in common,
and...
and that might be something
that I can do too.
I mean, fuck,
I have so many questions.
And I'll answer them as best I can.
Are you gonna help me be like you?
Don't even pretend.
Hi, Dexter.
Going for a little night swim.
Enjoy.
Who's she?
- That's my neighbor.
- She's cute.
Yes, she's cute.
You need to go home.
When are we gonna talk about...
I'll call you.
Look, something has come up
that I have to deal with.
My day job,
which is something you need to get.
Why?
I have money.
You're a weird guy
who lives with his mom.
You might as well be wearing a sign.
Look, all I'm saying is that you need
to have some kind of cover life,
something that makes you
look ordinary.
Yeah, right, yeah.
I get it, yeah.
Zach, I understand
what you're going through.
I will help you with this.
Okay.
Thanks.
Not a single sighting
since she disappeared?
Thank you.
Motherfuck.
What you doing?
Nothing.
Why do you look
like you just got caught?
Come on,
what are you doing back here?
You looking at porn over here
or something?
- No.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Company computer.
- Will you...
And I am the boss.
Hannah McKay.
Wayne Randall's girlfriend, right?
Got arrested a while back
for something,
then somehow slipped away?
Why you... why you looking her up?
None of your goddamn business.
Will you fucking back off?
- Jesus, relax.
- No, I'm seri...
You come in here all the time
and invade my personal space,
standing so close,
trying to flirt.
You're fucking
making me uncomfortable.
I didn't come in here to flirt, okay?
I just came in here to see
if you wanted me
to pick you up something
for lunch, that's it.
I'm all set.
Are we done?
Yeah.
Yeah, we're done.
You know what?
We're not done, actually.
See, Deb, you came to me
six months ago,
on an emotional wreck,
saying you just quit the force
and you needed a job.
I gave you that job.
I gave you good pay, good benefits.
I didn't ask a lot of questions.
I put up with a lot
of weird shit from you
because you're good at your job
and because I'm a nice guy.
So I'm really, really sorry
if this cramps your style,
but next time, maybe you want
to try a little gratitude
instead of always being
such a fucking bitch.
Now we're done.
There she is.
Vista Marina car rentals.
This is Stacy.
How may I help you?
Hi, Stacy.
This is Detective Cooper
over at Miami Metro.
My badge number is 143634.
We're investigating a hit and run.
We think somebody
who rented one of your vans
might have been a witness,
so I was hoping to get
some information over the phone.
I can fax you over a copy
of the warrant, if you'd like.
Oh, I'll just get it for you.
Do you have the license plate?
Yes, I do.
It's, uh, GLV43951.
The name on that account
is Maggie Castner.
The local address is
Slip 23, Vista Marina.
Thank you, Stacy.
Want the phone number?
Yes, that would be helpful.
813-398-2723.
You may have found her.
If so, a little too easily.
You think she wants to be found?
I think she wants
to destroy our lives,
mine and Debra's both.
Debra's very fragile right now.
Even the threat
of Hannah coming after her
could derail all the progress
she's making.
I won't let that happen.
So what's your plan?
Slip 23.
You have her number.
You could call.
I don't want to let her know
I've found her yet.
Why do you seem
less scared than excited?
Because Hannah doesn't scare me.
Maybe you need to rethink that.
They all look like nice apartments,
but I think you should work
things out with your brother.
Angel and I are gonna be fine.
I've just had it
with the whole "big brother
ruling over the roost" routine.
And the thing is...
What?
Well, just, most of these places,
I have to sign a one-year lease,
and I wasn't sure about...
About what?
Okay, I'm definitely not
pushing you, okay?
I'm just trying to be practical here.
If our relationship
keeps moving forward,
we might want to eventually get
a place together.
Yeah, eventually.
You don't have to decide now.
It's just something to think about.
Yeah, I'll totally think about it.
Okay.
I'm so sorry.
I-I blew that whole thing
out of proportion, I think.
I just felt like you were trying
to, like, get rid of me with a check.
I was just trying to be
a good, you know, father.
That was really sweet of you.
But it's my problem,
and I want to take care of it.
Well, I can respect that.
So we're cool?
Cool.
How about you and I
do dinner tonight?
I can't.
I have to work right after class.
You know, pay off the debts.
Wow, well, good for you.
Where are you working?
It's a sports bar
called lucky Pete's.
I can, uh, call you, though,
when I'm free.
We can get together.
Okay.
Sounds great.
The Hannah McKay I know
hated the ocean.
But it does make for an easy escape
into international waters.
Brave of her to be walking
around Miami like that.
Or maybe she's found someone
to protect her.
- May I help you?
- I'm just meeting some friends.
I'm sorry, sir.
Members only.
Oh, but I'm a friend of...
Even so, sir,
we have a strict dress code.
Call it a night, Dexter.
- You don't want to go in there.
- I do want to go in there.
It's their territory.
You'll be at a disadvantage.
I need to know what she's up to.
Dexter.
Is your father a member
at the Red Coral club?
Yeah.
It's full of old farts in suits.
Why?
Can you get me in there?
Tonight?
Yeah.
Sure.
Good to see you, Mr. Hamilton.
So what are we doing here?
Looking for someone.
I thought we weren't
supposed to be seen together.
This is different.
♪ ♪
You know her?
That's my ex-girlfriend.
Nice.
Who's the guy?
I'm gonna find out.
All right, you keep an eye on him.
You text me when he's coming back.
Got it.
♪ ♪
Hannah.
It's Maggie now.
You shouldn't be here, Dexter.
Well, I'm not leaving
until you tell me
why you drugged me and left me
on the side of the road.
Well, after what you did to me,
I'm not sure
that you get to ask questions.
But here I am, asking.
What are you doing back in Miami?
Well, I was about to enjoy a Martini.
You should probably leave, though,
before my husband returns.
Your husband?
You're married to that guy?
Yes.
I'm very lucky.
Yeah, well, he seems rich.
You were always a pragmatist.
Well, the money's nice,
I have to admit, but...
He has other talents.
Miles is the adventurous type.
What are you doing here, Hannah?
My husband will be back any minute,
and it's probably
in your best interest
that he not see us together.
Well, I told you, I'm not leaving
until you tell me
why you did what you did to me.
I see you've made a friend.
This is my husband, Miles Castner.
Dexter Morgan.
Maggie has told me about you.
Oh?
How you were her boyfriend,
until you betrayed her,
turning her in to the police.
Quite a predicament you left her in.
Shall we finish our drinks?
I think it's time for us to go.
Well, that's an excellent idea.
Make sure Mr. Morgan is given
whatever he needs.
Didn't you get my texts?
I warned you that guy was coming.
I know.
So why didn't you walk away?
I mean, I watched him.
I stayed on him.
I didn't fuck up in there.
I screwed up, not you.
You did exactly as I asked you to.
So what now?
Nothing.
I'll call you.
We'll talk tomorrow.
So that guy, are we...
Are you gonna kill him?
I only kill people who deserve it.
You here,
'cause something sure ain't right.
While them orphans
was camping in the woods,
something gave them a proper fright.
Miles Castner
made his fortune
in international casinos.
He has the power and the reach
to get Hannah
a new name, new passport,
but if she's as happy
as she seems in her new life,
then why is she here,
messing with mine?
Miles Castner...
What kind of name is Miles, anyway?
Don't be a chump, Zoomer!
Ain't no such thing as...
- Hey.
Hey.
Hello.
Harrison, hello.
That's it?
I remember when I used to get a hug.
Even I don't matter
when Rastamouse is on.
I checked in with Marshals, FBI,
fucking Homeland Security.
There hasn't been a single
sighting of Hannah McKay.
I'm hoping you've had better luck.
Yeah.
I found her.
She's married.
Well, there's someone
for everyone, I guess.
I hope he's sleeping
with one eye open.
What's her married name?
The guy she's married to
is worth $700 million.
He owns casinos.
The name, Dex.
Castner.
Miles Castner.
They're staying on his yacht.
I don't know what they're doing
in Miami.
Maybe he has business here
or something.
But he seems to know who she is,
even knows about her and me.
And she...
Seems to like him,
or maybe she just
feels obligated to him.
I doubt Hannah McKay
feels obligated to anyone.
It's got to be operational.
She needs a cover life.
It's not like it's a real marriage.
She can't actually love this guy.
Oh, my God.
You're still in love
with her, aren't you?
What?
No.
She's probably trying to kill me.
Trust me,
no one knows what it's like
to fall in love with the wrong person
more than I do.
But you better get
your fucking head on straight.
She is everything
that is wrong with our lives.
She is a vortex.
She is a black hole.
She sucks everything into her being,
leaving nothing behind.
We have got to get her
out of our lives.
I'm working on a plan.
Are you sure you can be objective?
One little toss
of Hannah's pretty blonde hair,
and you turn into a fucking moron.
Hannah?
Hannah is here?
Both of you?
Jesus.
Really?
Deb, I'm on top of it.
I'm gonna figure out
exactly what she's up to.
Are you?
Where is Hannah?
Right now, she's on a very big boat
with her husband.
♪ ♪
Niki?
Hey.
Hey, what are you doing here?
I came here to see you.
I didn't realize
this place was a breastaurant.
I mean, it is a sports bar.
It's just topless.
And I make really good money here.
Are you really okay doing this?
Yeah, it's not the best job
in the world,
but it's also not forever.
I'm fine with it.
I can tell that you're not.
Me?
Oh.
Look, I go to places like this
all the time.
- See?
- I...
Look, I've stared at a million boobs.
But until now,
I never considered them
to be... daughter boobs.
Daughter boobs?
Well, come on.
You know what I mean.
Guy, hey.
Her face is up here, okay?
Come on.
It's so sweet that you care.
I'm just gonna stay here
until something better
comes along, okay?
Yeah, I'll, uh...
I'll let you do your thing.
Do you want to have dinner
on my next free night?
Yeah.
That's great.
It actually makes sense, in a way,
that Dexter would have been
involved with another killer.
- Well, she's back.
- Mm.
And she poisoned us.
Who knows what the fuck else
she has planned?
What does Dexter say?
He's trying to figure out
what else she's up to,
but I'm afraid he's thinking
with the wrong head right now.
You're concerned for your safety.
And for Dexter's.
Let's take a step back.
From what you've told me,
if she wanted to kill you,
you'd be dead by now.
Well, maybe she just wants to prove
that she has control,
that she can kill us
whenever she wants to.
It's a very unsettling
feeling, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
So what is it you'd like to do?
I would like to take her
to Marshal Services
and have her the fuck arrested.
- But Hannah knows too much.
- Yeah.
But at least I wouldn't have to worry
about what might or might not be
in my morning coffee.
When the brain surgeon was out there,
a threat to me,
I-I could hardly sleep.
I trusted Dexter
to solve the problem,
and he did.
And if I can't?
Before you take matters
into your own hands,
be sure to consider all the
consequences of those actions.
The husband is a complication
I don't need.
I have to get Hannah alone,
in a situation I control.
Have you done the blood work
on the triple in Lummus Park?
Not yet.
There's the prints on the
pesticide bottle still to run
and the decomp over in Coconut Grove
- we still have to process.
- Yep.
Whew, we could use
an extra set of hands, right?
Someone lower level,
an extra warm body
to offset all the cold ones.
Don't you think?
I mean, at least to make a dent
in the paperwork.
Sure, I guess.
Excellent idea.
Zach...
What's he doing here?
Quinn.
Okay.
My client requests
that you cease and desist
this 24-hour watch you have on him.
He requests it.
I'd like you to back the fuck off.
You took these photos, Zach?
Yeah, and those
are just the best ones.
Quinn, do you have anything to say?
Yeah, I think the kid's guilty.
I'll answer for you, Detective Quinn.
On behalf of the entire department,
I can assure you that we will...
Well, how did you put it, Zach?
"Back the fuck down."
- "Off."
- Yeah, that too.
Right, Detective Quinn?
- Right.
- That's right.
Gentlemen, let me show you out.
What the fuck were you thinking?
That rich asshole
is walking around, free.
We have nothing on this kid.
That's why I was following him.
Yeah, if this was any other case,
I would personally sign off
on the overtime.
But this one...
Let it go.
That's an order.
By the way, me and Jamie
are moving in together.
You're what?
You're doing what?
Hey, uh, you got a minute?
Uh, make it fast.
Okay, well, Dexter and I
are buried in that glass box.
We need an assistant.
I don't know about that.
Wait, hold on,
we've been under budget
the last three quarters.
- It was Dexter's idea.
- Okay.
Part-time.
You're one hell of a lieutenant.
The photos were a nice touch.
Thanks.
I thought so.
Well, now he's off my tail.
We can get down to business.
Find someone to... you know.
Eventually.
What do you mean, "eventually"?
I mean...
Long before my father taught me
how to do what I do,
he taught me how not to do it.
Why would I want to not do it?
Timing is everything.
One thing you need to learn...
The first thing that I had to learn...
is to wait.
Control your urges.
Channel them appropriately.
Dexter, I can't wait.
I can't control it.
Yes, you can.
You're gonna get your chance,
Zach, I promise...
but the only way I've survived
as long as I have
is by being careful.
I'm gonna teach you how to do that.
And then?
And then you'll be able
to do what I do
and get away with it.
What do you want?
I saw you with your son.
Maggie never mentioned him.
Hard to picture her
as the family type.
There's nothing going on
between Hannah and me.
Good.
Then listen.
I'd sooner see her in prison
than lose her.
Do you understand?
Because I could call a few people
and ruin your life.
And being a family man,
I'm sure that's not what you'd want.
People are so impatient.
Dexter, what are you doing?
This is something you don't want
to get in the middle of.
He said he'd sooner see her
in prison than lose her.
If that's what he thinks
this is about,
she's the one in danger.
I thought you were going to find out
if Hannah was a threat
to you and Debra,
not if Miles was a threat
to Hannah.
Why can't I do both?
Your flowers.
That's the thing about plants.
You don't look after 'em, they die.
So... what's up?
Miles just conononted me
at a gas station.
God.
He likes to be dramatic.
Is he a threat?
A "chop you up and toss you
in the ocean" kind of threat?
No.
But he could
make your life miserable,
have people look into you
and follow you around 24/7.
He sounds like a great guy.
And you're really
in a position to judge?
Why did you marry him?
Because he was there
when you weren't.
I needed him, Dexter.
I met him a few years ago
when I did some flowers for him
at an event,
and he found
my background intriguing.
I could tell that he had
a bit of a crush on me,
so when I made my little escape
and when I had nothing
and when I was desperate,
I kn t that he could give me
a whole new life,
a new identity,
money.
Plus, he makes me happy.
Bullshit.
If you're so damn happy,
what are you doing back here?
Why did you drug Debra and me?
- You know, I think you should go.
- No, answer me.
I wanted to make sure
that you weren't gonna
put me in jail.
I had to see if you would come to me.
Which I did, and you still
haven't told me why.
Because it doesn't matter why
anymore.
I changed my mind.
About what?
I wanted you to kill Miles for me.
You what?
He's possessive and controlling
and obsessed with me to the point
where he follows me everywhere.
I might as well be in prison.
If I were to try and leave him,
he would... he would just turn me in.
Why haven't you dealt
with this in your usual way?
Because his family already thought
that I was some kind of gold digger
when we got married.
If he was gonna drop dead suddenly,
for no reason,
I would be the first person
that they would turn to.
And once the cops get
a good look at me...
You wanted me to make him disappear.
I thought you might feel
like you owed me.
- Owed you?
- You didn't have to turn me in.
- You ruined my life.
- I did...
You know, it doesn't even
matter anymore,
because like I said,
I changed my mind.
And this is my problem,
and I'm gonna find
a way to deal with it.
Why did you change your mind?
Because the moment that
I saw you there, unconscious,
I realized that,
despite the shitty way
that it all ended,
you were it for me, Dexter.
I've never felt that way
about anyone before or since.
You're the only person
that I can be that honest with.
And I didn't want to ruin that
by manipulating you
into doing something
that might be bad for you.
It was the same for me.
No, just leave it at that.
I have to go before Miles
finds out where I've gone.
- Hannah...
- Good-bye.
Hey.
Um, can I borrow that
high-tech G.P.S. tracker thingy
that you have?
Please?
Yeah.
Being nice
when you need something, huh?
I'm not surprised.
Sorry that I overreacted earlier.
I know that you're interested.
You act like you are.
But, Jake, you don't want
to get involved with me.
You have no idea who I really am.
I just want a chance to find out.
Can I help you?
Is that your car?
Um, it... it's my brother's car.
I think I left my sunglasses
in the passenger seat,
and he's not answering his phone.
Your brother is...
Dexter Morgan.
He lives in the building.
Oh.
Oh, you're Dexter's sister.
- I'm Cassie, his neighbor.
- Debra.
Oh, fuck, you're Cassie
who went out with him, right?
Really?
He mentioned me?
You look surprised.
I am.
I, uh, I guess I figured
he thought I was the worst date ever.
He didn't exactly follow up.
But he's always nice to me
when I see him.
He's kind of impossible to read.
Yeah, that would be Dexter.
Oh, okay, good, I was starting
to think it was me.
Nope, definitely not you.
Hey, um, since I've got you here,
what's his deal?
Jamie seems to think
he's not over his ex-girlfriend,
which totally makes him
more attractive to me,
'cause apparently, I have
a thing for unavailable men.
Sorry.
That was an overshare.
That's all right.
I get it.
It's so crazy, right?
I meet this totally nice guy
who's completely into me,
and I'm still hung up
on the mysterious man next door
who hasn't called.
I don't know you...
At all, actually.
But you seem
like a normal girl, you know?
If I were you, I would probably stick
with the guy
that's obviously interested.
Trust me, Dexter is not a mystery
that you want to solve.
Okay.
Yeah.
Sorry about all that.
It's all right.
Have a good one.
See you.
- Hey!
- Hey.
You could've come inside.
I just got your text.
Oh, well, you know,
I think I've seen enough
of that place, you know.
So...
What brings you by?
I wanted to let you know
that a lab assistant position
just opened up at Miami Metro,
and it's yours if you want it.
What does it pay?
$13.75 an hour, plus dental.
I make a lot more money
than that here.
You did say that
this wasn't your first choice
- as a line of work.
- Yeah.
I figured you'd jump at the chance
for a future that didn't
include pole dancing.
I'm not gonna be a stripper, Dad.
Whoa...
Hey, it just slipped out.
That's okay.
Well, listen, just do me a favor.
Just think about it, okay?
I think it would be good
for the both of us.
Okay.
All right.
- Bye.
Well, that's probably best
for all involved.
Two psychopaths together...
Never a good mix.
Hannah's not a psychopath.
She has feelings.
I'll have to take your word for that.
Anyway, I called you
over here tonight
because I'm concerned about Zach.
He came to me today
in a very agitated state.
I know, I didn't let him
kill his father,
and now he's feeling the urge
more than ever.
And how do you plan to handle it?
I was ten years old
when Harry told me
what my future would be.
I didn't kill until I was 19.
Zach can wait.
He just doesn't know he can.
- Apples and oranges, Dexter.
- Sorry?
You thought you had no choice but
to wait because your father told you to.
But you were just a boy
who'd never taken a human life.
- Zach has already killed.
- Don't get me wrong.
I'm glad you took him off your table.
But the moment you did,
Zach became your responsibility.
He's relying on you, Dexter.
You need to take this very seriously.
Hi, you've reached Zach Hamilton.
Please leave a message.
Hey, Zach.
It's Dexter.
Let's meet tomorrow afternoon,
2:00 p.m.
I'll come to your studio.
It's good that Hannah's leaving.
I have enough on my plate
trying to turn a young killer into...
Someone like me.
Miles knows that Hannah and I
saw each other yesterday.
If Miles will do this to me,
what will he do to her?
So who are you tracking?
I'm just kidding, obviously.
I don't want to invade your privacy.
I just want to see
if you need anything.
No, I'm good.
Okay.
Jake.
I know I can be
kind of a dick sometimes.
You don't deserve that.
It's okay, most people think
I'm a dick too,
so I guess we're even.
This past year hasn't been my best.
The truth is,
I wouldn't be surviving it
if it weren't for you, so thank you.
You're welcome.
Dexter?
Come on, what the fuck?
Dexter!
It looks like he's not home.
Can I give him a message?
Yeah.
Fuck him.
Hey, babe.
Good hunting?
Yeah, I found a couple dresses.
I think you'll really like them.
Nice.
I'm guessing today's shopping
went better than yesterday's.
- About the same.
- Really?
That's surprising,
considering there probably isn't
much of a selection
at your old greenhouse.
What are you talking about?
You were with your friend.
Dexter Morgan.
Well, he a... he asked to see me.
He wanted to make sure
that I was all right
after you confronted him,
and I told him
that everything was fine,
that we were very happy together,
end of story.
Don't lie to me.
I know the truth.
Oh, Miles, I told you,
I don't care about him anymore.
So you won't be too upset then.
About what?
About what yesterday's excursion
is going to cost your friend.
Miles, that's unnecessary.
- You've made it necessary.
- No, please, don't hurt him.
"Don't hurt him"?
Why, because you love him?
No, I promise you.
I'm not ever gonna see him again.
He's the reason you insisted...
- Stop it.
- On coming with me to Miami,
returning to a place where...
- Ouch!
- - You're a wanted criminal.
Miles, ow!
He's the unfinished business
you mentioned.
I want you to know I forgive you.
We're going to make a new beginning.
I've already told the crew
we're leaving tonight.
We'll sail thehe coast,
then cross the Atlantic,
just the two of us,
for the rest of our lives.
That's how much I care about you.
No, Miles.
Stop it, please.
You'll never have to leave this boat.
Stop...
I've given you everything!
You belong to me.
No, stop it.
Get off me!
♪ ♪
♪
I-I tried to run,
but...
He just grabbed me.
I didn't mean for it
to happen this way.
Are you hurt?
I'm okay.
We need bleach, bags,
something to cut with...
an axe or a saw
or something like that.
You think you can get me those things
without letting the crew know
that anything's wrong?
Yeah, I think so.
Yes.
Wait, you need to change.
- All right.
- Hannah.
It's gonna be okay.
I'll take care of everything.
I believe you.
So that's how
you make people disappear.
Give or take a plastic room
and a kill table, yeah.
Yeah, I remember that part.
Do you ever wish
that you had followed through?
With killing me?
No.
Ever wish you had?
I was never going
to kill you, Dexter.
It's just...
Well, I knew I couldn't
live with Miles for much longer,
and...
Unlike you, I don't
actually enjoy any of this.
So what's next?
I told the crew that Miles was going
to New York for a few days,
so that should buy me some time.
What's wrong?
I have to go to a crime scene...
At my apartment building.
- What does that mean?
- I don't know.
I have to go.
Please don't leave town
before we talk again.
I won't.
This could be my apartment.
Cassie.
Dexter?
What happened?
I don't know.
I just got here.
Cassie and I,
we were supposed
to have a date tonight.
I'm sorry.
I know you were friends.
You okay to work this?
Yeah.
What do you see?
She was bludgeoned.
See those marks on her neck?
Someone held her down
and beat her to death.
God.
Norma Rivera was bludgeoned.
Is it possible Zach did this
when I was with Hannah?
Harry was a good teacher to me
because he was normal, human.
But can anything good come
from putting two killers together,
whether it be student and teacher
or whatever Hannah and I have?
Or will it always end the same way,
like this?
Sync and correction by Mlmlte
www.addic7ed.com