( dog barking )
( helicopter whirring )
( chattering )
( radio alarm )
* Incarcerated...
Rise and shine!
C'mon, man,
get up!
Oh, boy.
C'mon, get up!
It's a school day,
y'all gonna be late!
Let's go,
get to school.
Go, get up,
c'mon, man.
- Damn, Wallace.
- Damn, Wallace, nothin'.
Little hoppers like y'all
don't go to school,
and soon enough they
goin' be callin' around
and all y'all end up
in foster care.
Y'all want
foster care?
Just climb your
little black asses
back in them beds, then.
Get out
of my way, man.
Damn, too early
for this shit!
( children laughing )
( sirens blaring )
Narcos?
Naw, rollers, man.
Yo, where's breakfast at?
Here, man,
take your chips.
I want two bags.
No, man,
you ain't gettin' no two.
Quit being greedy.
Take your chips!
Ah, c'mon, here,
take your juice.
C'mon, man.
Where mine?
Go share with Tee-Tee.
C'mon, man.
Where's
your book-bag?
Teacher ain't
give no homework.
C'mon, man.
( music playing )
This is the worst case
suicide I've ever seen.
That's him.
You see?
That's him,
right there.
That's Omar's boy.
Go ahead, man.
( theme music playing )
* If you walk
through the garden *
* You better
watch your back *
* Well, I beg
your pardon *
* Walk the straight
and narrow track *
* If you walk
through Jesus *
* He'll save your soul
* You gotta
keep the devil *
* Down in the hole
* All the angels sing
* About Jesus' mighty soul
* And they shoot you
with your wing *
* Keep you close
to the Lord *
* Don't pay heed
to temptation *
* Oh, your hands
are so cold *
* You got to
keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole
* Way down in the hole.
What the fuck
can I tell him?
Whatever the man
wants to hear, Jimmy.
Whatever
he wants to hear.
Prodigal son.
Major, we got a good shot
to clear a couple cases here.
One thing--
We're not here
to talk cases, McNulty.
I don't care
about your cases.
Sit.
Relax.
I'm a reasonable guy.
In fact, everywhere I go,
people say to me,
Bill Rawls, you are
a reasonable fucking guy.
- Am I right, Jay?
- You are reasonable, sir.
Yes, yes, I am.
And because your sergeant
knows me to be reasonable,
he came in here
a couple weeks ago
and reasoned with me,
right, Jay?
We reasoned,
we did.
We reasoned that despite
his negligible Irish ancestry
and a propensity
to talk out of turn,
Jimmy McNulty
is a good worker,
probably worth saving.
- Major, I'm not--
- He's a good-looking
kid, huh?
Do you know what
we do here, McNulty?
What we do here?
That was one of them,
what-do-you-call-its,
a question you don't
really have to--
A rhetorical question.
You were being rhetorical.
Rhetorical
and reasonable, sir.
We work murders cases
here, Detective.
We work them
as they come in.
One at a fucking time,
it's called a rotation.
You're up
'til you catch one.
When you catch one,
you step down,
you work it for a while,
someone else steps up.
It's a simple, but effective
way to do business
in a town that has 250
to 300 cases a year.
Yes, sir.
But if someone gets
it into his head to leave
the rotation,
it puts an unfair burden
on the other detectives,
who have to pick up
their casework.
Overworked cops
make mistakes,
mistakes lower
the unit-wide
clearance rate.
And that can make
someone who is
otherwise
as reasonable as me...
Unreasonable.
( chuckling )
Detective McNulty,
I expect to see your ass
back here next week
when your shift
rotates to night work.
* Dreams come true,
maybe it'll be me and you *
* Things go up
and the beat goes on *
* Like one of those nights
that goes on too long *
* Maybe one of those songs
that could've got *
* Cut the fuck off
a long time ago *
* My friends, still as I lent
like I knew you wanna see *
* Should've just
followed the laws *
* The hip-hop laws,
you know those laws *
* There's laws
of hip-hop, kid *
* You should've read that book
that I recommended *
* 'Cause if you did,
you would see... *
( pager beeping )
* If you don't
have a hip-hop license *
* You're trying
to be rhyming... *
He's up early today.
A lot of pager activity
last night too.
( reggae music playing )
No woman
takes that long.
Yeah, but
I look good, right?
Wow, you did
all this, huh?
Burn an egg or two,
ain't no thing.
Yeah, my mama
always said, don't let
'em get to cookin'.
Once they get
into your kitchen,
ain't nothin' left
to do but give 'em
a key to your house.
I don't want no key.
I don't want no house.
And your mama don't
know shit about me.
He looks
just like you.
Yeah, he do.
Where's his mother?
Around the way.
Yeah, you friends?
Oh, you know,
she want a key.
She want a house,
she want a car,
she wants some new clothes,
a necklace,
she wants
some pocket change,
you know, a trip
down to the shore,
and she want a credit card
with her name on it.
Ain't no such thing
as free, right?
When it come to pussy,
ain't no free.
I gotta go.
You're working
on this one.
Lines on the other
two pay phones aren't in yet,
but you'll
get 'em tomorrow.
So, we up?
On the low-rise
pay phones, yeah.
Let's hear.
Woman:
See what I'm talkin' about
is he ain't paid no one
and he just think
he right to do it.
- Man: Huh.
- You see how it go?
So I ain't got shit,
I ain't got it.
But, damn, you know.
Thinkin' he all that because
he got his family thing.
- Who?
- Dee, talkin' about Dee.
Hey, it was
getting good.
- It's unmonitored.
- It's what?
It's unmonitored.
We can't listen
to a conversation
on an unmonitored
pay phone.
What's that mean?
We got a tap on
the courtyard pay phone.
By tomorrow we'll be up
on two near the high-rises.
But we can't listen
to anything unless
we know one of our targets
is using the phone.
So, we gotta be out there
on those rooftops for hours,
watching these assholes
talk on the phone?
Yep.
It's more bullshit.
Detective,
this, right here.
This is the job.
You know, when you came
downtown to CID,
what other kind of work
were you expecting?
So, what are you
gonna do?
Well, I can't get
back here in a week.
This case
is taking off.
You tell Rawls that?
No.
McNulty,
line three.
Yeah?
Where at?
800 block,
in the rear.
Yeah, I got it.
Thanks.
Yeah.
( barking )
( laughing )
( police radio chatter )
11-22.
Man on radio:
I'm still out here
waiting on a lab unit.
Do we have an ETA?
Negative,
they're all out.
Christ.
Damn dog
got Norris too.
And you didn't
think to warn me?
Too much fun
not to.
Damn.
Yep.
He one of yours?
We found him
with the Kevlar,
like the one Worden
caught last week,
so we thought maybe
it might be a connection.
- Yeah, it connects.
- How so?
Don't have a name,
but he's part of
a stickup crew,
took off a stash house
last month.
- My guy, Barksdale,
is coming back on them.
- In a big way.
Jesus, they must've killed
this kid four or five times.
Cut him in a dozen places,
burned him with cigarettes.
Goddamn torture-fest
is what it was.
Doesn't look like
your scene either.
Fuck him up somewhere else,
dump him here for all to see.
Anything
we can use?
Not yet. But we're up
on some phones.
If I hear anything,
I'll let you know.
11-22.
- Man on radio: 22.
- Anything yet?
Or we just stand
around here and let
this guy go ripe on us?
Are you waiting
for crime lab?
Over an hour.
Only two units on the street
and both of 'em are up
at the city council
president's house.
What happened there?
Someone stole
his lawn furniture.
They're up there taking
pictures of an empty patio
and dusting the backyard
gate for latents.
I kid you not.
I swear to God,
you show me the son
of a bitch
that can fix this
police department,
I'd give back
half my overtime.
He was all
cut up and shit,
his insides
was hangin' out.
That's fucked up, yo.
I mean, damn.
Sometimes, you gotta
send a message, yo.
I mean, yo, when you
picked up that phone,
what you think
they was gonna do, huh?
Shit, all that shit
is in the game, man.
You know that.
Yeah, like you
and that girl, huh?
- What girl?
- The one in the apartment.
- Come here, man.
- The one you told us
about, remember?
I mean, I liked
what you said about all
that killing, you know.
Especially that part
about how it ain't
got to be like that.
Just sell the shit
and move on.
Get me a ginger ale
and get something
for yourself.
Boy:
Yo, Day, c'mon.
Yeah, I know,
I remember that, but it
ain't like that, is it?
- ( pager beeping )
- Yeah, I know.
I know it ain't.
Thing about it was his eye,
his eye was blown out,
and the other one
was open...
and, yo, Dee,
it fucks me up!
It's like
he's looking out,
like he sees
everything, you know?
Don't think about it.
I can't.
Fuck!
Yo, let that shit go.
Just let it go.
Yeah, Barksdale kid
on the line.
He's beeping someone.
Who threw that?
You got a good arm.
Go deep.
( phone ringing )
- Yo.
- What up?
- Yo, you ain't him.
- Hold on, hold on.
Hey, yo, Strings,
it's Dee.
Strings:
Yeah.
Dee:
Yeah, you hit me?
Yeah, yeah, um...
I wanted to know,
if you know young hopper,
the one they got down there?
Which one?
You know, the fool
who dropped the man
with a punch, you know?
Oh, yeah, yeah,
what about him?
He got some
promise, right?
What you mean?
Enough to bring
home, right?
You know, man,
whatever.
A'ight.
( phone clicking )
( beeping )
They bringin'
Bodie home.
The young boy
who was with him,
light-skinned kid
from the cemetery.
- Greggs: Where?
- In the alley behind
the 800 block of Argyle.
- Right across
from the low-rises.
- Shot?
- Stabbed, beaten, burned.
- Jesus.
- Yeah, we gotta
get with Omar.
- Yeah.
( tires screeching )
Impressive.
It's not often that I see
respondents come so prepared
for a juvenile
commitment meeting.
In addition to those
signed statements
from Preston's sponsors
at the Police Athletic League,
I also have a photostated
copy of a cashed check,
which indicates that he is
enrolled in the GED program
at the Baltimore City
Community College.
Can I ask how this young man
is able to afford, not one,
but two attorneys
from your firm, Mr. Levy?
This is pro bono,
Your Honor.
My firm is making it
a priority to identify
a number of city youths
who are in crisis
and to undertake efforts
to reorder their lives.
Excuse me, but I can't
help but notice
that your client is under
a delinquent petition
for the sale of narcotics,
and further,
for assault on
a police officer.
Beyond that, he walked away
from a JSA facility.
Your Honor, my client
stands ready to acknowledge
that he was involved,
for a time,
in the sale of
a small amount of drugs,
a transaction for which
he received no remuneration,
having been manipulated
by older traffickers
in his neighborhood.
That was a mistake,
Your Honor.
So noted.
However, we will contend
that it was Preston
who was the victim
of a brutal police beating
indications of which
are still evident on him,
Your Honor.
He struck back,
wildly and in
self-defense,
Your Honor.
- And the walk-away?
- Preston was heavily medicated
when he left
the Cheltenham facility.
In that state,
Your Honor,
he was simply trying to get
back to see his grandmother.
Did you know
what you were doing
when you left
boys village, son?
( clearing throat )
Naw, I was, uh...
I was messed up.
Anything else
you'd like to add?
Um, just...
I don't know, uh...
I'm ready to be good.
Pending a hearing on
these charges to be scheduled
within six months,
I'm putting the respondent
on home monitoring
with his grandmother.
Ah, Your Honor.
I'm afraid Mrs. Broadus
doesn't have a telephone
for any
monitoring calls.
She's on a fixed income,
Your Honor.
How about he calls
his probation officer
twice a week?
Cool, whatever.
Your Honor.
- ( dogs barking )
- ( sirens wailing )
( chattering )
Yeah!
Yo, Bubbles,
what's the game?
- Hey, Johnny.
Up an' about, huh?
- Yeah.
- Huck.
- Bubs.
Where's the scam
at here?
Ain't no scam.
Thank you, ma'am.
What you got here
is an honest day's work
for an honest day's pay.
Right, Lavell?
Oh, Mr. Straight-time,
Bubbles.
Gotta give a little
somethin' back when
they least expect it.
Me and Huck here,
we got somethin' on too.
- We got a plan.
- No.
For real,
for real.
Yo, we're gonna take off
on the Copper House.
Damn, Johnny.
Your first few days out and
you goin' get all dramatical.
- The Copper House?
- Got to be got, homes.
- Yeah, what about the fence?
- Fuck the fence.
Fuck the--
- ( laughing )
- How about the dog?
Fuck the dog.
Yo, all that time I was
resting got me thinking.
Yo, got good
to me, too.
Copper House...
gracious.
I gotta roll.
Okay, cash me out.
Yo, if you ain't got dreams,
Bubs, what the fuck you got?
Thank you.
C'mon, dreamer.
( chattering )
( phone rings )
- Yeah?
- One of ours on the line.
Got 'em.
Is Carv still there?
Hold a sec.
Carv, call for you.
Carver:
Yeah, hello?
You ain't gonna believe
who I'm lookin' at right now.
Again he walks off?
Ding, round three.
( pay phone ringing )
- Yo.
- What up, man?
Yo, Stink, what up.
Yo, where your
manners, fool?
My bad, yeah.
You need to keep
your fuckin' head, boy.
Forgot it.
Um, yo, what's up?
Where you at?
I don't know,
where you at?
Oh, I'm down in the pit.
Just came home.
I don't see nobody around,
I just wanted to know,
you know, what was up.
Ain't nothin',
goin' late, man.
Oh.
Just catch us
tomorrow, man.
- A'ight.
- A'ight?
Yeah,
a'ight, later.
( clicks )
- ( beeps )
- Non-pertinent?
How do you log that
non-pertinent?
No drug talk.
They use codes to hide
their pager and phone numbers.
And when someone
does use a phone,
they don't use names.
And if someone
does use a name,
he's reminded not to.
All of that
is valuable evidence.
Of what?
Conspiracy.
Conspiracy?
We're building something
here, Detective.
We're building it
from scratch.
All the pieces matter,
all right?
( tires screeching )
Shit.
Ow, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Are you
fucking serious?
Ah, fuck.
You keep walking
away from JSA,
we keep
kicking your ass.
I'm all right with that,
if you are.
Look, I ain't walk away
from nowhere, man.
Check my back pocket.
Home monitoring?
Yeah, man,
if you ask questions
before y'all start
wilding on niggas,
you might save
everybody some trouble.
How the fuck
are you home?
Yeah, you know
what I mean.
Juvenile judge, man,
he saw my potential, okay?
He expects
big things from me.
Yeah, like what?
I don't know,
college, law school,
medical school,
all that good shit.
Seriously,
how are you out?
Look, I'm gonna
tell you somethin'.
Okay, this is just
my opinion, but, uh...
the juvenile system
in this city is fucked up.
It's a big-ass fucking
joke, no offense.
Fucking fuck.
Hey.
Look, give me a ride
down to my grandma's,
we'll call it even.
Man:
Hey, yo, hold up!
In back, fucknuts.
Man:
Get a line real quick.
( sirens wailing )
Jay!
( music playing )
( honks horn )
Get your ass out of
the street, bitch.
- Hey.
What's up?
What you need?
Little late in
the month for this shit,
don't you think?
What you mean?
My aunt, she hit
the Match-Four.
You stealing
from me, Cass?
What?
Raymond,
you look fresh today.
Got laid last night,
that's why.
Oh, yeah?
Your asshole
still hurtin'?
- Call Jimmy.
- What's up, boss?
Rawls finally got around
to reading the office reports
that McNulty
tried to give him.
He wants arrest warrants
for Deidre Kresson
and the two project murders
that match up to that gun.
I know.
Ah, c'mon, jay.
Be right on this.
I can't, it's Rawls.
He wants warrants today.
All right, no problem.
So, who the fuck are
we supposed to charge?
You got a witness that puts
D'Angelo Barksdale
at the scene of the murder,
the night of the murder.
You've got a ballistics match
between the Kresson girl
and the two dead
mopes in the project
where Barksdale hangs.
Run with it.
This weak-ass shit is not
gonna get past a grand jury.
Charge the mope
and work it more afterward.
Call Jimmy,
let him know.
Dee:
Yo.
All right, listen up,
new deal.
Wallace, you goin'
be on the stash now
with LaTroy
and Peaches.
And what
about Sterling?
Sterling, he gonna
be down on Preston
lookin' out for a while.
- Cassandra too.
- What happened?
- Nothing.
- Why you wanna
change up then?
Nigga, I got to explain
shit to you now?
Stringer Bell's
pager number?
Stinkum's too,
I'm pretty sure.
Very sweet.
If they moved around a bit
more, we'd have problems.
But they're a little lazy,
you know.
Tend to go to
that one pay phone
in the courtyard
a little too much.
Jesus.
He's lit at 9:00
in the morning?
Or from
the night before.
Detective?
Detective Polk.
Yeah, it's McNulty,
Bunk paged me.
All right.
Why did you even
come in today?
I had some--
To pretend that
you were here?
To fill out
a run sheet?
I know I missed a couple days
last week, Lieutenant.
I got run sheets
from you every day
for the last two weeks.
Twice in
Carver's handwriting.
Twice it was Prez.
Once it was McNulty,
I think.
They covered for you.
But I won't.
Well, Lieutenant,
I, um...
I don't know,
I'm not really up for this
drug thing, you know.
Maybe if Mahone was here,
I could get into it more.
Learn some new tricks,
I'm...
oh, hell,
Lieutenant,
why don't you just
send me back to property
and keep
everybody happy?
Send you back
to property crimes,
so you can binge
for two more weeks?
I'm not doing that.
Lieutenant, please,
look I...
You were dumped
on me, Augie.
But it ends there,
I don't dump people.
You either go out
on those rooftops today
to watch pay phones
with the rest of this unit,
or you go over
to the medical office
and check yourself in.
- Medical?
- For alcohol abuse.
Either dry yourself out,
or go up on those rooftops wet.
Take a few minutes
and think on it.
- Where'd they go?
- Who?
Lieutenant...
we need a file cabinet,
or two.
The paperwork
from this, I mean...
there's a lot of it.
Lieutenant?
Sir, um...
I'm going to...
good luck
with the case.
( reggae music playing )
Fucking Rawls.
He's fucking up
the case to get to me.
No, he's fucking it up
for three paper clearances
on prior cases, Jimmy.
It ain't personal.
All he's got is D'Angelo
at the scene through hearsay
and a ballistics
match to a couple of
unrelated drug murders.
How can
he charge that?
Baby, he can charge
anything he wants
to get credit
for the clearance.
Grand jury doesn't indict,
he drops the case,
keeps the stats.
I need to go in there
and tell him what
the fuck he can do.
- No, you don't.
- No, I'm trying to build
something here,
all Rawls can think to do
is stick a finger in my eye.
- You talk to Landsman?
- Jay can't fix this.
Rawls told him to have
the warrants typed
and ready by morning.
You're telling me
he's gonna charge murders
he can't prove
just to get the stats?
And fuck up our case
in the process.
We give up
the ballistics info
and the motive for
the Kresson killing
in the charging documents
and Avon Barksdale,
he's gonna change up.
And what he don't change
up, he'll clean up.
Somebody needs
to tell Rawls that.
Oh, Rawls couldn't
care less.
Rawls wants me home
and he wants the stats,
that's all.
Then we take
this to Daniels.
- Daniels?
- It's his case,
he'll fight for it.
- Daniels won't do shit.
- He plays stiff every
now and then,
- but he's a good man.
- Are you kidding me?!
Daniels has been
trying to put the brakes
on this for weeks now.
This'll be his
new excuse to close shop.
Well, look, you guys
got to make your move soon.
All right?
I'm sorry to say.
- Freamon?
- All right, man,
take care.
- We tell Daniels.
- Fuck Daniels
and his fucking
ass-kissing, up-the-chain-
of-command ambition.
What other choice
do you got, huh?
We go to Daniels.
If he fights, he fights.
If he gives
it up to Rawls,
then fuck it,
we were never gonna do
the case anyway.
All right, come on.
( rock music playing )
Oh, God.
Fucking idiot!
Come on, get up,
stupid, let's go.
I'm hurt, man,
I'm hurt.
What are you doing?
Leave me alone.
What are you on,
dope or something?
- Mostly, yeah.
- Come on, get up,
get up.
Oh, ow! You tryin'
to rip out my guts
or something, man?
You tryin'
to kill me, man?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Where you goin'?
Buddy,
I gotta get help.
You can't. You can't
leave me here, man.
You gotta stay with me.
Stay with me.
All right, let me get you
over to the curb.
Go get help, man,
what are you doing?
- Stay there, stay there.
- Aw, Christ.
Damn, boy, that all
come out of you?
- Onion soup, Campbell's.
- Yeah, come on.
Run, Forrest, run.
You could go to Forester,
or the deputy ops.
Why come crying
to me?
Why not go to your friend
the judge?
I don't see a circuit court
judge being able to argue
the city homicide commander
out of three murders,
even if the cases
are all weak sisters.
It's put up or shut up
time, Lieutenant.
Either you step up
or you send us all home.
So, this is on me?
I don't see anyone else
in charge of this detail.
Rawls is a major.
Rawls is an asshole.
My point is,
he ranks me on this.
( scoffs )
The chain-of-command might
mean nothing to you, McNulty.
What I tell you?
( music playing )
( helicopter whirring )
( sirens wailing )
Yo, how we doin'?
We doin' good.
You know, if you
say we doing good.
What's up?
So, the word is out about
these stickup boys, right?
Yeah, yeah,
y'all bein' heard.
A'ight.
There goes shorty
right there.
What's up, man,
you know?
I'm a man
of my word.
You know, I said
it was 4,000 on Omar,
2,000 on each
on the younguns.
This bein'
a team effort,
I'm puttin' $500
in the boy's hand
for doing the scope,
I'm putting $500 in your hand
for doing the relay,
I'm putting $500
in Wee-Bey hand, Bird hand,
for doing
the musclin' up.
How you doin'
with that other thing?
What?
Everybody
a little pressed, right?
Oh, yeah,
yeah, yeah.
You know,
ain't no surprises yet.
I cut everybody loose
on Friday,
and they all just
a bunch of beggin'-ass
bitches, you know.
I mean, ain't nobody
showed no money since.
You gonna keep it hummin'
though, right, cuz?
Yeah,
you know it.
Oh, oh, you got
your hands up,
you got
your hands up?
You keep on doing,
like how you're doing,
we'll be talking about
points on the package.
A'ight?
A'ight.
Keep it hummin'.
Yeah, mos def.
A'ight, baby.
Take it light,
but take it.
Yeah.
- 40 cents.
- No, not 40 cent
a foot, no sir.
No sir, look,
respectfully,
I got to tell you.
For 40 cent a foot,
you might as well
go ahead
and drive on out
to Home Depot,
right, and pay them.
They gonna charge
you, what, 45, 45,
50 cent a foot.
For copper
that isn't stolen.
Look, all right.
35 cent,
35 cent a foot.
And that's all
in respect I have
for y'all.
What y'all tryin'
to do in the our
community with these,
these quality
domiciles here.
30 cents a foot,
take it or leave it.
I understand the interest
in clearing these cases, I do.
But charging
those murders now,
and putting
the information
that we have into
the charging documents.
I just call 'em like
I see 'em, Lieutenant.
Three murders,
same gun.
We got this Barksdale kid
right at the scene on the one.
We're up on a wire.
We're starting
to pull good information.
You charge these
prematurely and Barksdale
will change up on us.
The work
we've already done.
I can't tell you how to run
your case, Lieutenant.
I can only run my own.
Major...
I'm asking
as a favor.
As a favor?
Yes, sir, a favor.
In that case...
no!
Sorry.
You got off
from work early today.
Yep, work sucks.
Are we eating dinner
with you?
Why not?
Mom was
cooking lasagna.
So, we'll go to Little Italy,
get some lasagna at Sabs.
You never cook.
Yeah, cooking sucks too.
( pager beeping )
Who's this?
Man: Hey, yo,
I want to see him.
Who?
Brandon, my boy.
Copper House, yo.
Wasn't shit.
My plan, Bubs.
Johnny had a plan.
( laughing )
Get out the way,
motherfuckers,
this here white boy day.
- I got a plan too.
- What?
We gonna wait
for that cheap-ass,
speculatin' motherfucker
to put that
good copper line
back into them row
houses he fixin' up.
And then, before
the drywall get up,
we creep back in
there and steal that
shit right back.
30 cent a foot.
Got to come back
at a motherfucker
for that, you know?
Yeah.
You good?
I could top off
with one more.
Just one,
just one more.
Johnny got it.
I'll be back.
( video game sounds )
It's my night
with the kids.
( ignition starting )
( Johnny shouting )
You ain't gonna
buy nothin',
'cause I ain't
do nothin', man.
Why don't you just
leave me alone, man?
A white man can't
walk down the street?
What's that about?
Come on, man.
That sucks, man.
It's profiling.
What, it's 'cause
I'm white, right?
Why don't you
just let me--
oh, man,
what the--
what's that?
What's that?
That boy
ain't got no luck.
Hey.
So...
what you gonna do
with your money?
You know,
what you should do,
you should take
the whole roll
and go do somethin'
nice for your girl.
You do have
a girl, right?
Yeah, well, anyway,
you got enough money
to get yourself one now.
Yo, why you punk Sterling
like you did?
I mean, he did get shot
behind this shit.
I didn't
punk him, yo.
So, why you drop him
to lookout?
Cass, too.
'Cause they
was thieving, yo.
Both of them.
They got pissed
'cause I wasn't
paying them.
So, Sterling,
he started shaking
up the vials,
handing off to Cass.
She was selling
on the side.
You ain't
tell anybody?
I mean,
Stinkum, Bodie?
They don't know?
If I tell 'em,
what you think
they gonna do?
They gonna take
a baseball bat
to Sterling.
Probably one
to Cassandra, too.
There's too much drama,
right?
So, I just took 'em
both off the stash.
So, why didn't
you pay us?
That wasn't right.
Listen, man.
Stringer thought
we had a snitch down here.
You know, with the jumpout,
Omar, all that shit.
So, he told me to punk
y'all for a little while,
see who was
still holdin' money at
the end of the week.
Was they snitchin',
Sterling and Cass?
Naw, man,
just thievin'.
( TV playing )
Hi. I'm homicide.
Okay, you two sit
right here, okay?
Don't wander off.
Um, Dad?
What?
You know,
it's a school night.
Mom said
we had to--
I know, I know,
we will.
Okay?
You stay there.
( video game sounds )
( Omar screaming )
Woman on radio:
64 Charlie to Central K.
You up to this?
McNulty:
Pay it back, Omar.
Pay it back.
( police radio chatter )
I'm saying, why we ain't
in no real police office?
We're a little
like you, Omar.
Out here on our own.
Playing the game
for ourselves.
Hard way
to go sometime.
Sorry about
your friend.
Avon is
one sick bastard.
Of course he had
his reasons.
Greggs:
For one thing,
y'all did take his stash.
For another, he was
looking for you, Omar.
That's what all
the cigarette burns
were about,
broken fingers,
cracked forearms.
He wanted your boy
to give you up.
An address,
a street.
Kid had heart.
Yeah.
I know you want to go
to wherever it is
you lay your head
and pick up that sawed-off
you like so much
and go on the hunt.
That's how a man like you
wants to carry it.
And you wouldn't
be wrong.
Greggs:
No, you wouldn't.
But one man with two barrels
ain't enough, Omar.
Now you gonna do
what you gonna do,
but whatever else
you can give us
on Barksdale
and his people,
well, that can go
to hurting them, too.
McNulty:
Just throw us
what you can.
Hey, look, let me tell
y'all something, a'ight?
What I do, I do!
Straight like that.
So ain't no sense
in y'all even troublin'
yourselves over that.
'Cause, man, the way
I feel right now, today!
Hey, what y'all
need from me?
When'd you
last see Brandon?
Tuesday.
'Round 7:00,
maybe later.
He was on his way
to Mondawmin,
then the Greek's
after that.
Everybody talkin'
'bout he got snatched
up from there.
From the Greek's
on Baltimore Street?
Yeah, he like to play them
pinball games to death.
Greggs:
He go alone?
Oman:
Yeah and I ain't
like it none neither,
but you know, you can only
treat a young man like a boy
for so long
before they buck,
you know what I mean?
When Bailey got killed,
you must've figured
that Barksdale was coming
back on you, right?
Man, Bailey?
Please.
That nigga's enemies
got enemies.
I just figured he tried
his hand on the wrong corner
without us
and got dropped.
But you were worried
about Brandon, right?
Omar:
Look, in my game,
you take some
care and you play it
the safest way you can.
But it ain't about
no hiding forever.
You heard?
And frankly, you been
in this as long as me,
you do the thing
on your name.
Anyone gonna
come after Omar,
they gonna know Omar's
comin' after him.
Oh, indeed.
So, who came
after Brandon?
Heard it might've
been Wee-Bey.
Boy Stinkum.
And Bird,
he was down
with the snatch, too.
Greggs:
So, what can you
give us on the towers?
Omar:
What you need?
Check it,
7:56, Tuesday night,
you got an incoming call
to D'Angelo Barksdale's
giving him the number
of a pay phone,
Westside exchange,
numbers encoded, right?
Three minutes later,
you get another call from
the low-rises to that number.
Then a half a minute later
you get another call
from the low rises
to a pager number
we know is
Stringer Bell's.
Well, I'll be damned.
Finally, you get another call,
probably from a pay phone,
probably Stringer Bell
calling back
coming on into
the low rise courts.
45 minutes later,
another call,
this one from
the same pay phone that
went to D'Angelo's pager
to start the
whole damn thing off.
You see that?
This is the murder,
right here.
This first number,
the one they sent
to D'Angelo,
I'm thinkin' this
comes from a pay phone
over by the Greek's.
He's on you.
We're up on those pay
phones Tuesday night,
we catch that murder.
Shit, we get there
before the murder.
It's all here
on the pen registers.
This one calling that one,
that one calling back.
We're up on those pay phones
when we should be,
and we have them cold.
But we're not up
in time, are we?
In this case, we're never
where we need to be.
( door slams )
Bad time for y'all?
He fight,
but you arrest.
You saw him
get arrested?
On Tuesday?
Tuesday, Tuesday,
yes, yes, Tuesday.
By the police?
The police arrested him?
Cuffs,
they handcuffed him.
Mmm.
How about
these guys?
Were they there
with him?
No, no.
No?
No, he fight,
you arrest.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
It's a match.
No.
I need help.
Rawls ranks me.
Lieutenant, think
what you're doing here.
You're gonna
cross Bill Rawls,
as ruthless a fuck
as we have in this
department,
and to do what?
To fight for a case
the Deputy of Operations
doesn't even want.
No.
I like my career,
thank you very much.
Greggs:
In the cemetery,
you were telling us a guy
by the name of Bird
killed the working man?
Omar:
Yeah, that man
who testified.
William Gant, right.
Yeah, Bird did that one,
for sure.
- How you know?
- Everybody know, man.
Nigga walked up
behind the man
and shot him
straight in the head.
The whole blessed
projects saw that much.
And Bird worked
for Avon?
Yeah, as one
a his shooters.
Liked to use this
real sweet gun he got.
A 380 from Austria
or Australia,
or something like that.
But I know
he love that gun.
- A 380?
- Yeah, a 380.
You get him,
you get the gun,
'cause Bird too dumb
to throw a gun like
that off.
- A gun alone ain't enough.
- Oh, no?
He goes to court,
testifies he bought
the gun on the street
after Gant was killed.
Come on, now,
so, what be enough then?
Eyeball witness.
Some kind of corroboration
for what you're telling me here.
- Okay.
- Okay, what?
I'm your man.
You saw the murder?
Yeah.
You can ID this man Bird
as the shooter of William Gant?
And you ain't afraid
to go into the court downtown
and testify against
one of Barksdale's people?
Omar don't scare.
The fact is that while
Lieutenant Daniels
and his merry band
are lost in the swamps,
playing with beepers
and pay phones and body mikes,
my people have
developed information
that ties Barksdale
to three killings.
D'Angelo Barksdale,
not Avon.
D'Angelo,
on behalf of Avon.
The victim is identified
by our witness
as being involved
with Avon Barksdale.
Sir, we're developing
information.
You're dancing
around this thing.
I'm charging
three murders.
You charge those cases,
my investigation folds.
And what's more,
not one of those cases
is strong enough for court.
You know that.
So, we bring
the Barksdale kid in,
throw a little mindfuck
at him and the case
becomes stronger.
You've had him
in the box twice before.
He's gonna go for less
the third time around.
So, we recanvass,
develop fresh witnesses.
The case
I charge on today
can be twice as strong
by the trial date.
We get a conviction,
we roll little boy Barksdale
into big boy Barksdale,
then we go home like
good old-fashioned cops
and pound
some Budweiser.
This...
is bullshit!
It was
McNulty himself
who made the ballistics
match on these murders
and he's telling me
to fight this.
He knows you don't have
a viable prosecution.
So do you,
so do I.
Enough!
Look, I've got no love
for your wiretap, Lieutenant.
I'm spending 2,000 a day
over the unit operating budget
to staff the case.
And Major Rawls here
is offering a chance
to leverage Barksdale
through a murder prosecution.
Why not jump on this?
Because if
Major Rawls is right,
then he will be just
as right a month from now.
And if the wire
doesn't give us a case,
he can charge all
the murders he has.
We lose nothing.
But if he's wrong,
if he can't convict,
or if the Barksdale kid
doesn't flip,
then it's too late
to do anything else.
Avon Barksdale
changes up his pattern
and the wiretap dies.
And at that point,
there isn't gonna
be a thing
that you or me
or Rawls here
is gonna be able to say
to that goddamn judge.
You wanted
to see me, Major?
McNulty does personal
business on the clock,
I want to know.
He cheats on a run sheet,
He runs any kind of game
at all, I want to know.
Major, the man's
an asshole,
but he doesn't do much
other than work.
He's got this fuckin' case
in his gut like it's cancer.
He does no wrong?
He doesn't drink anymore?
Doesn't drink on duty?
Doesn't drink
and drive, Detective?
Major...
You gotta help me
on this, Michael.
Daniels:
The murder warrants
are on hold.
The deputy gave us
another month.
Also, whoever that was
you brought in here today
gave himself up
as an eyewitness
in the Gant murder.
Who, Omar?
And Greggs said
to tell you she'd write
it up in the morning.
Lieutenant.
Thanks.
It cost you?
( music playing )
( theme music playing )