Previously on Dystopia.
- Those
machines, what do they do?
- Find the young Philip Edier.
I'm gonna give you a
way to remember me.
- Biocorp,
headquarters, it's here.
- So, the ID chip,
the prototype for it.
- The girls know
to wake me up first,
that's why I'm on the clock.
- You girls seem
worth fighting for.
- You're in the hospital.
- What, what year is it?
- What year do you think it is?
- I wanna go there myself.
- It's not that easy.
- Then make it easy!
- And finally,
tonight's top story.
Today, Nobel Peace Prize
winning Biocorp made history
by administering
the cure for cancer,
available to the entire
world's population
in exchange for their
compulsory enrollment
in the ID chip
program, which allows
for increased
population security.
Biocorp's CEO stated,
"It takes a brave man
"to knock on the
door of evolution
"without knowing what
lies on the other side.
"But we've taken
the first brave step
"to improving our
children's future today.
"Go through the door
and what awaits you
"on the other side is
something worth fighting for."
- Why don't you just
kill us all now?
Huh?
Kill us now, kill
us all, go ahead.
- I need to undo the
damage they've done.
Who gave these men the right
to change the course of history?
Who made them gods?
- So what, now you're
gonna play God?
- They're trying to save us all.
If you stop what they started,
we're all doomed to extinction.
- You mean your friend, Thomas?
Let me tell you about him.
20 years ago he kidnapped
me, he held a gun
to my head and he cut
this into my neck!
So don't pretend
that I'm the bad man
in some pathetic
childhood story.
I didn't want the
world to end like this!
But from my perspective they've
always been in the past.
So how the hell do I know that
they didn't cause all this?
- You heard her.
They're trying to save us all.
- This sort of power shouldn't
be reserved for just anyone.
- Then you're okay
with this power?
- Of course, I am a
government official.
- It's your government that
caused it in the first place!
- That's why I trust you'll
never let anything happen to me.
Because without me they will die
and you'll never know
if you can be saved.
- The Butterfly Effect
works both ways.
- What's that you're
saying, Grandpa?
- Time's not an arrow
always going forward.
The ripples can travel
forward or backward.
- I'll bear that
in mind, Grandpa.
Cut him loose.
- You'll need to wear this.
- What is it?
- It's how we get you back.
This lets us monitor
your condition
as well as tell
you when you are.
You ping it here, it
sends us the signal,
and we bring you back.
So don't lose it.
I don't know what
your intentions are,
but please, for the
sake of mankind,
keep in mind that for every
catalyst there is a reaction.
For every cause
there's an effect.
- I'm counting on it.
Let's get on with it.
- I hope that every American,
regardless of where he lives,
will stop and examine
his conscience.
This nation was founded by men
of many nations and backgrounds.
It was founded on the principle
that all men are created equal.
And that the rights of
every man are diminished
when the rights of one
man are threatened.
Today we are committed
to a worldwide struggle
to promote and
protect the rights
of all who wish to be free.
In short, every American
ought to have the right
to be treated as he
would wish to be treated.
As one would wish his
children to be treated.
But this is not the case.
- Come in.
- Sorry to disturb
you, sir, madam,
but there seems to be
a situation developing.
- What is it, the Chinese?
- No, sir, it's domestic.
The details are
few at this point,
but it seems there's
been an attack on
a Biocorp officer and
a seige is developing.
- A siege?
- Apparently, a group of
rogue scientists have killed
a Biocorp officer
and they have...
- Have what?
- Well sir, they seem to have
built a machine of some type.
No one knows what it
does, but it seems people
are hooked up to it, the
scientists themselves.
- And that's all we know?
- Yes, sir.
- Well, who's in
charge down there?
- The local officer
on the scene.
Apparently, they breached
the building and he's inside.
- You get yourself
a regional commander
out there right away.
- Yes, sir.
- Before this thing escalates.
Find out who they are
and why they're there.
- Yes, Mr. President.
- Okay.
- Adam, run program.
- Program initiated, David.
- That's it.
He's a time traveler.
Hey, hey, can I check on them?
I can kill Philip by
severing the upload link.
The guards won't
know the difference.
It'll just look like
he's still asleep.
- What do you think?
- I think that they
would find out eventually
and if we're not out of
here by then we're done.
- We'll wake up Nico and
Thomas, we'll fight our way out.
- Well, how do we do that
without them noticing?
- I haven't figured
that part out yet.
- Even if...
- Temporal
displacement complete.
- He's fine!
That's all good, his
brain activity's normal,
his heart rate is fine,
everything's fine.
So?
- What about the
Butterfly Effect?
- Yeah, it could screw up
everything for them as well as us.
- So we wake him up
and we kill him now.
It won't affect the
future or the past.
- Maybe Philip will have
about epiphany there
and realize what they're
really trying to do.
- I wouldn't bet on that.
- So, we verified your identity.
Nicholai Stone.
We found your father, they're
trying to contact him...
- No, no, don't, don't
contact him, he's...
Listen, he suffers from
a rare mental disease.
He makes up stories,
gets confused.
- I empathize, my father has
cancer, but it is protocol.
- What type of cancer?
- Brain, don't
change the subject.
Who are you?
- Look, let me
level with you, Doc.
I haven't talked
to my dad in years.
You're right, my name
is Nicholai Stone
and the reason why
my records show
that I'm 10 is because
I was born in 2007.
- Look, I don't know what
you're talking about.
I'm in no mood for games.
- I'm not, either,
look, please wait.
I need your help, okay?
You seem like a good man.
I need time to explain.
I need you to keep
an open mind because,
look, I'm the least
craziest person that I know.
- I'm listening.
- I'm a scientist
from the year 2037
where life as I know it is
on the verge of extinction.
Women are completely infertile
and not a child has
been born in years
that has survived
longer than an hour.
- I think you need to
get some more rest.
Look, we'll do a CS scan,
check for any cranial
hemorrhaging...
- Look, I don't suffer
from delusions, okay?
Do you know the company Biocorp?
- Yes, they make most
of our equipment.
- What about them?
- Exactly!
They're the reason
why we are infertile!
- How do you know this?
- Because I told you,
I'm from the future!
Humanity is on the
verge of extinction.
There's no children, there
is no cure, there is no hope!
- This is why I'm gonna need
a psychiatric evaluation!
- I'm telling you the truth!
I know you might
think it sounds crazy
and you think I'm
delusional, but I'm not.
You are a doctor, your
job is to save people.
You have a chance right now
to save the entire world!
- Look, I need you to relax!
If not, I will call security.
Do you understand?
Do you?
- Yes.
- Good!
Look, I'm gonna get you
all the help that you need.
Yes, Frank, he needs
to be seen right away.
He might be perfect for
that study you're doing.
Oh yes, full
manifested delusions.
At 9 a.m.?
Thank you, I'll keep him
sedated for an hour or so.
Alright, Frank, thanks.
See you tomorrow.
- Why are you here?
Really?
- Okay.
I'm from the future.
20 years from now, to be exact.
Me and my friend
have time traveled
back here to fix something.
Something that threatens
the very existence
of the human race.
- The doctor said your
friend said that, too.
- Well, he's telling the truth.
And so am I.
- I know you believe
that, but it's not true.
- You have to open
your eyes, here.
Some things are true whether
you believe in them or not.
You have no idea what's coming.
In a couple of years the
government is gonna try
and make it law that
every single human being
gets a chip implanted
under their skin,
but it has the
unfortunate side effect
of making the whole
planet infertile.
Where I'm from not a single
child has been born in 20 years.
- I know you believe all this,
the time travel and the future...
- What if I'm right?
Think about it for
just a second, okay?
What damage can I possibly
do to a dying old man
that the world hasn't
already done, huh?
But if you release me, let
me go, let me out of here.
But I can't do it alone.
I need your help.
Please, release me.
- I can't.
- I should go check on him.
- Make it quick.
- Be ready.
- Everything will be okay.
Don't attack them, trust me.
- We have to.
- You will gain nothing.
You will lose everything.
- You're a kind man.
- I'm just an old fool trying
to save two beautiful
young ladies.
- What is all the
whispering about?
- He's not feeling well.
Do you mind if I make
everyone something to eat?
- Can I help her?
She's really weak.
- No.
- For some reason I believe you.
- Thank you.
- Then let's get right to it.
- What's that for?
- This is mine.
- And what are you
gonna do with it?
- If they come in
here I want them
to know that you
held me hostage.
- Okay, deal.
Thank you.
- Hey, Jen.
Who's your friend?
- Uh, this is actually an
old friend of Dr. Mangan's.
- Father or son?
- Uh, both, actually.
- Did you call it in ahead?
Yeah, here it is.
- Where is Dr. Mangan?
- I guess he's still
out on a consult.
- He's always really busy.
- Was he supposed
to meet you here?
- No.
- It doesn't matter.
- No, it doesn't matter.
It just proves that it's
like father, like son, huh?
- It seems that way.
I love your accent.
- Isn't it great?
- Oh, ladies are just
flattering me, I'm gonna blush.
It's really quite
ordinary where I'm from.
- Well, to us it's a
break in the every day.
You guys can go ahead
and go on through.
- Thank you.
Would you give me a
moment alone with him?
- Sure.
- Thank you, nice to meet you.
- It was nice to meet you.
- Nico!
I've only got a minute.
- I never thought I'd be
happy to see your ugly face.
- What the hell happened,
how are we still here?
- I don't know, they could
wake us up at any minute.
- Well, did you send
the signal to David?
- I did, I sent him the signal
right before we put
ourselves under.
- Then there's a problem.
- I don't know.
- At their end!
- Their end, but I don't
know how long we've been out.
I'm just afraid they
could wake us up
at any minute, the
power could get cut...
- If the power gets
cut we're dead.
- No, we don't
know that for sure.
We don't.
- Okay, but what we do know
is that we gotta leave.
- I have a plan.
- What is it?
- The doctor, his
dad has cancer.
- Real cancer?
- Yeah, like real cancer.
This is 2017, they don't
a cure for three years.
- Okay, and?
- So, what?
We can save him!
That'll save us.
- Save the doctor's father, why?
Why would we, what about
the Butterfly Effect?
- I thought about that but we
need the doctor to believe us.
We need him to believe us.
- Oh, I don't know, Nico.
If the cure for cancer isn't out
for another three years think of
all the damage we
could do by letting
the cat out of
the bag too early.
- Okay, what, saving millions
of people, is that so bad?
- This isn't a question
of right or wrong, Nico.
This is about causing
too much damage,
ripping our own future apart.
- What's so bad about that?
Think about all the mothers,
the fathers we would save.
All the children we would save.
The possibility of them living.
- I thought we couldn't rule
out the Butterfly Effect.
That's a rule you made up.
- I'm not ruling...
- You said it yourself!
I'm not ruling it out, okay?
I'm just saying we
can't be slaves to it.
We've been here
interacting with people.
You know how much damage
that has caused already?
Are you thinking?
- That is different, okay?
We weren't trying to
cure cancer before.
- If you're so worried about it
why don't we just
kill ourselves now?
Is that what you want?
- No, I want us to
be careful, Nico,
and remember that
we're not gods.
- I'm not saying we're gods.
I'm just saying we...
I'm saying we need to try.
- Come on.
- Okay.
- Now get your ugly face
over here and cut me out.
- Stop calling me ugly.
I'll take care of the father.
You find drugs to
put us to sleep.
- Attention, a violent patient
has escaped on
Wing C, code blue!
- Can I have security, please?
Attention all units.
Our suspect is at large
inside the hospital
and under delusions,
he's violent.
Use extreme caution.
- Nice to meet you, Frank.
It's your lucky day.
This means you won't be
able to have kids, Frank.
I'm hoping that's okay.
You'll be alright.
- Freeze!
- Suspect apprehended.
- Hands up!
- ICU Room 4, second floor.
- Hey, hey!
- Put it down!
- Alright, alright.
- Turn around.
Hands on your head!
On your knees.
You, go!
Hands on your head,
hands on your head.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Heading to second floor.
- Fine, fine.
- So, Nicholai,
where did you go?
- To visit my friend.
- What, fully clothed?
- Well, the robe gave me chills.
- Unfortunately,
this escape attempt
solidifies my feeling, you're
not ready to be released yet.
Paranoia is a frequent symptom.
I have some medicine
to help you rest.
- Look, I don't
need medicine, okay?
I'm not crazy.
- Nicholai, you are
not from the future!
Time travel does not exist.
And until you start
to realize that
I can't trust you to
function within society.
- Look, I can prove it.
Just give me a chance.
- Hold him down.
- Wait, no, no, listen!
I can save your father.
Listen to me, I can
save your father!
Look, I have a cure,
you have to believe me!
Look at me, I'm not lying!
I have a cure, I have a cure!
I'm not lying!
I can save your father!
I can save your dad!
- Hold him down.
- Get, no!
Get, no, no, no, no!
Believe me, I can cure,
I can cure your father.
Believe me!
- There you go.
- Believe me.
No, no, Jenny.
Jenny!
- Jenny?
- Mm, smells good.
- Help yourself.
- Hello, Nicholai.
- Who is it?
- Don't you recognize me?
- No.
- My name is Philip Edier.
- Where's my wife, my sister?
- So you do know who I am?
- Are they alive?
- My men are looking
after them and you,
just for everybody's protection.
If anything happens to me and I
don't return
they'll be executed.
- What are you doing here?
- Oh, I am here to
help all humanity.
To set right what you've
attempted to undo.
- Thomas should have killed
you when he had the chance.
- Oh, is he here with you?
Nearby, maybe?
I'm just dying to
meet him again.
- He spared your life.
He could have killed you.
- You have no idea
what he did to me.
What he made me.
- Commander on site!
- I knew it.
- If it were any
other day I'd be
irritated by another
uninvited guest.
He can't by any
worse than the last.
- Report.
- Sir, this is how
they time travel.
- Thank you for that
penetrating analysis.
- The other two
are the only ones
that know how the
machine operates.
This is his team.
They're not telling us much.
They claim not to
know enough to effect
any changes on the device.
- Edier believe this?
- I'm unsure, sir.
He followed them into stasis
to find the answers for himself.
- What orders did he leave?
- If we were to receive
signal from the stasis chamber
we're to start executing
hostages one at a time.
- What you may not be aware
of is that time travel
not under state
control is illegal.
- You expect me to believe that
the government has
access to time travel?
- You expect me to believe that
your friends created
this out of thin air?
- You're bluffing.
- Perhaps, but thank you for
confirming one of my theories.
We have located the source
of temporal disturbance,
but it's a lot more complicated
than we first thought.
Tell me everything you know.
- I already told him everything.
- Yes, well, I can't very well
much talk to him now, can I?
Edier may have flair,
but he's reckless.
Luckily for him, I
don't have such faults.
- So, why are you really here?
- To follow you.
To ask questions
that need answering.
- Like what?
- What's the key to
staying here without
being dependent on a
stable body in 2037?
- I don't know.
But even if I did,
I wouldn't tell you.
- Indeed.
You see, Nicholai,
I want to stay here.
This is a much better reality
than the one we came from.
- We already lived
this reality once.
- As children, that's nothing.
What power do children have?
None.
And just think of all
the pain they cause.
- So, are you saying
the infertility
of our future is a good thing?
- Oh, who knows?
This insistence that
children will somehow
save us from our inhumanity
towards each other.
You see this, hmm?
Your friend Thomas
did that to me,
in this time, when
I was a child.
So how can he and
you claim to lament
the loss of children
when you do this to them?
When you create
monsters like me?
- You're a coward!
You're running away.
We can fix the future.
Help me.
Help me fix what Biocorp
is doing now, here,
before it happens.
- I wonder what would
happen, Nicholai,
if I was to kill you now?
Would you just wake up in 2037?
I guess there's only
one way to find out.
- How's it looking?
- Not good.
They're even military out there.
- Not the police?
- No, well, the guy is dressed
in black with big guns,
so I don't think
it really matters.
- I don't wanna be here anymore.
- Okay, wait, hold on.
I can't let you go just yet.
I need you for just a
little bit more, okay?
What are you doing?
Relax, okay?
- I don't wanna stay
here, I'm scared.
- Look at my face.
You're just scared,
I'm scared, too.
Do you think I'm gonna hurt you?
- No.
- Do you think I'm gonna let
anybody out there hurt you?
- No.
- Okay, that's because I'm not.
The only person in
danger of hurting
anybody is you right
now, and I need you.
Jen, I can't do this alone.
I need you.
- Hey.
- Hmm?
- You okay?
- Yeah.
I'm okay.
- That's my girl.
Now I need you to leave.
- There's a whole
SWAT team out there.
- They won't hurt you, okay?
They'll see you're unarmed.
You'd look like just a hostage.
Go.
- Okay.
- This was a real good idea.
- What in the name
of God is going on?
- Doctor, you and your staff
should not be here,
it's not safe.
- Safe, what are
you talking about?
- We have a hostage situation.
One of the patients has
taken a nurse hostage.
- Which patient?
- An English guy.
- Who'd he take hostage?
- He took Jen, he said he
knew you and your father.
- Is this true?
- Certainly not.
- Then she must be under duress.
He used her to get into the ICU.
- Why would he...
- What is it?
- What was he doing in the ICU?
What'd he do to my father?
- He's safe.
- That's not what I'm asking.
- I saw him inject
something into
the IV and I called security.
- And that's
when we stopped him,
but whatever it
was he was doing...
- Is he still in his room?
- Yes, he's stable,
we're running tests.
- Come with me, ma'am.
- You have one minute to tell
me everything I need to know.
- Go to hell.
- One minute before
I signal my men
to execute either your
wife or your sister.
You see, I like my men to make
their own decisions
from time to time.
- You already know everything.
Otherwise you wouldn't be here.
- I need to understand
all about this
so I don't have to rely
on you and your friend.
- If that were the truth,
once I tell you, I'm dead.
There would be no
reason to keep me alive.
- Well, there are worse
things than just killing you.
You understand?
- How you doing, Dad?
- Alright, I'll just send my
men the signal to execute...
- Okay, okay, okay,
no, wait, wait, just...
It's all about
temporal mechanics.
We were trying to invent
teleportation, not time travel.
- Teleportation?
- So, I don't know anything.
I wasn't trying to find
this, this found me.
And I'm learning as I go.
- Am I expected to believe that?
- You know what, believe what
you want, but it's the truth.
David's the only one
that's went back and forth
and you're the only one
who's talked to him.
- Well, pretty soon, there'll
be someone else going back
because I ordered my men
to wake you in 30 minutes.
- Why?
- Because when you
get back there'll be
a guy waiting for you.
He's real good at
getting information.
He'll have a lot of
questions for you.
- So you're sending me
back to get tortured?
- And to prove the process
to get back to 2037
actually works.
- It does work, David
already went back.
- No!
He was awake when I arrived.
You think I'm gonna
trust his word?
- So you came all the way here
without knowing
you can get back?
- It was a risk I
was willing to take.
Come on, start talking.
- I have to be in stasis first.
If I'm awake when this
happens then I die.
- So what do I do?
Come on, clock's ticking.
- Okay, well, I
have to be asleep.
And I need drugs to
make this happen.
This applies to you,
too, so don't send
a signal until you're
ready to be under.
Do you understand?
- You try anything,
people will die.
You understand?
- Yes.
- What happened?
- His pulse-ox is up to
97 and still climbing
so we took him off the O2.
- We need a CT scan
done right away.
- It's already ordered.
- CBC with tox screen?
- Just came back negative.
- Well, that's preliminary.
- What are you talking about?
- That man injected my father
with a substance,
poison perhaps.
I'm just trying to find
out what damage he's done.
My father has a
Stage 4 brain tumor.
- We ran the CBC and
the tox screen twice.
It came back all clear.
- Well, perhaps it was...
- No, I mean he came
back clear of everything.
- Everything?
- I don't know what
to tell you, we ran it twice.
- What are you trying
to tell me, is he cured?
- We won't know until
we run further tests.
But I can say I haven't seen
him looking so well in months.
- So are you trying
to tell me that some
other patient injected
your father with something
and now his cancer
might be gone?
- That is a very
real possibility.
- What the hell?
- But I've never seen
a case of heart rate,
blood pressure, blood oxygen
level and overall power,
return to someone with
little time to live.
- We gotta find this guy!
- Look, it happened,
you can't just...
- Doc, Doc, don't worry,
we're not gonna shoot him.
But, whatever happened,
whatever miracle,
we really need to
talk to this guy.
Team!
- Good news!
I have been ordered to wake
Thomas with the adrenaline shot.
- No, he'll die!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
My sources tell me I am to
wake him up in 10 minutes.
He will be prepared to return.
- And how the hell
do you know that?
- We know everything
we need to know.
What can you
possibly understand?
Rabble, that's all you are.
Which one is Thomas?
- I don't know.
- Don't try me.
- Okay.
- No!
- Stop, you're gonna kill him!
- I am going to put the
adrenaline shot in both of them.
One will win, the
other will lose.
Which one is Thomas?
- No, Jenny, don't!
- Open your mouth.
- No!
- Open it!
- Lauren!
- Tell me now.
I am going to kill
each of you one by one
over the next 10
minutes until you speak!
Or shall I wake them all now?
- Young man, please,
have mercy on
these innocent people,
they're harmless!
- Be quiet, old man!
- Please don't harm
them, let them go!
- Stop it.
Not so tough now, tell me!
- No!
- Three!
- Two!
- Wait!
I'll tell you.
This is Thomas.
- Are you sure, old man?
- As sure as the fact
that you'll be dead soon.
- Alright, have it your way.
Prep two injections!
- Wait, what, no, no!
- I don't care if
they're ready or not!
We're going to
execute them anyway
for murdering a
Biocorp employee.
They're already dead.
Might as well just finish
them off now, right?
- Okay, okay!
I'll tell you whatever
you wanna hear!
- Oh, that wasn't
so hard, was it?
Philip has a more exciting
way of executing you.
- No!
- Much more brutal
than a gunshot.
Besides, we really should
interrogate him first.
He may hold all the answers.
I think I'll just
watch the show.
- What is this?
Dummies?
- No, it's a
simulation facility.
- You're running out of time.
If you don't get into
stasis you'll be a dead man.
- I know.
- What are you looking for?
- Pills, tranquilizers,
anything to put us under.
- You got 'em, come on!
You're not thinking of
backing out on me, are you?
- Look, see?
Right here.
Okay?
Alright, um, first I have to...
- You son of a bitch!
You just signed the death
warrant of all you hold dear.
- Okay, alright!
- Game's over.
- Alright.
- Syringe, now!
- I got it.
- On the gurney.
Come on.
Do it!
- Okay.
- System shutting down.
- Not such a harmless
old man now, am I?
- Nicholai connection lost.
- No!
- Get the power on!
- Thomas connection lost.
- Please, don't, wait!
- Fix it now!
- Goodnight, sweetheart.
- Distress detected.
- Wake him up!
- But how?
I can't, the link
has been severed!
- Do it!
- There's nothing you can do!
- Do something!
- Like what?
- Or I will!
- Please, just wait!
- Room clear!
- Secure the room.
Father!
- Nico!
- Father, what happened?
- No, don't!
- We weren't sure if you
were gonna send the signal.
Maybe I should have waited.
- You arrived just
when you were meant to.
- Don't!
- Get off!
- You okay, are you okay?
- This is all your fault!
No!
- Sir?
- Why aren't these men cuffed?
- They surrendered to us, sir.
They said they're
patients and friends
with the man in ICU 4.
- How about this guy?
- No, no, no, no,
these men are with me.
I've been trying
to tell you this.
They're patients of
mine and I can vouch
that they had nothing
to do with this.
Everything they say is
pretty much the truth.
- So, that's your
story and that's
what's going in my report?
- Of course, your report
should reflect the truth.
Let's get our patients
back into their rooms.
Right this way.
- Is this who you spoke of?
- Protect them, my son.
This is our duty.
- Who are you?
- We're the resistance and
we're here to help you.
- Who are you?
- Hello, son.
- How you doing, Dad?
- I never thought
that hospital food
could make me feel as
good as I feel right now.
- Dad, these are the gentlemen
who helped save your life.
- How can I ever thank you?
- It's all good.
- You see, the fact
that he couldn't
save me was killing him.
- He's a good man.
- Don't try to eat too
much at once, okay?
- You just stop fussing
over me and find me
a room where I can
watch a baseball game.
- You got it, pops.
You got it.
As you can see, I owe you far
more than I can ever repay.
- Well, perhaps we can pull
in a big favor one day.
- I doubt that's
possible, but I will try.
- I'm gonna get the adrenaline.
- No, wait, what
if you kill them?
- We have to bring them back!
- No!
- We have to, they're gonna die!
- They will only die here if you
wake them up when
they're not ready.
- What?
- You'll kill them for good.
Forever.
- Well, we can't
just do nothing.
- That's exactly
what you must do.
Exactly what was asked of me.
They're alive, but their
connection's been severed.
- So you knew them all along?
- So you didn't show up
at my door accidentally.
- I owed Nicholai
and Thomas a favor.
- What favor?
- Doesn't matter now.
My debt's been repaid.
- So, you knew them in the past?
- I did.
They're alive, but to you
they're trapped in 2017.
Nicholai entrusted me
with something to do.
Travis will take you to it.
It's in my room.
Jenny, Nicholai
loved you very much.
He wanted me to tell you.
- Thank you.
- Thomas told me
to tell you to look
under his bedside table.
Now, I've done all they asked.
Give me some time
with my own son.
- Of course.
Let's go.
- My son, I love you.
- I don't know what to do.
- You protect them.
Your grandfather
promised them we would.
- Tell Mom I love her.
- Yes.
- Now what we're
gonna ask you to do is
not only to save our lives,
but the lives of
billions of people.
- Maybe the whole future
of the human race.
- Again gentlemen,
I'm only one man.
- And we're just two.
- Okay, what do I need to do?