Previously on Dystopia.
- We have to bring them back.
- No!
- We have to, they're gonna die.
- They are trapped in 2017.
- It's people like
you, scientists,
ruined the whole world.
- Apparently, a group
of rogue scientists
seemed to have built a
machine of some type.
People were hooked up to it,
the scientists themselves.
- We have located the source
of temporal disturbance,
but it's a lot more complicated
than we first thought.
- See I owe you for all
more than I can ever regret.
- Perhaps we can pull
in a big favor one day.
- Look carefully, my son.
This is our duty.
They're alive,
but the connection's
been severed.
- Stop!
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
Freeze!
Dispatch, we got a code 6-33.
Suspect is heading north
on Washington Street.
C'mon, let's go.
He's right there!
Stop!
- Hey! Open the door!
- Come here, come here.
- C'mon, hurry up, hurry up.
Come on, come on, come on!
- Put your gun down.
Put it down. Put it down.
Put it down!
Step away.
Get up! Step away.
Don't try anything stupid.
Don't you try anything stupid.
Put this on.
Come on!
- You're making a big mistake.
- Today, BioCorp made history
by releasing the
cure for cancer.
Available to the entire
world's population
in exchange for their enrollment
in the ID chip program,
which allows for increased
population security.
The scheme, supported
by the President,
is said to usher in a new era
of world peace and prosperity.
The President stated,
"The future belongs
to our children,
"and the steps we take today
resonate throughout time.
"Let us be brave and
head into the unknown."
And that's all for tonight.
- And we're clear.
- Hi babe.
Hi!
- We need to haul ass quick.
- We can't just leave him here.
- There's a platoon
of BioCorp soldiers.
They'll be on us in a heartbeat.
- Can't we protect
them or hold them...
- We gotta go!
It's now or never.
Nicholai and Thomas are
alive and well in 2017.
- We gotta go.
We can rebuild everything.
- We got to go!
- We're just going
to leave them here?
- Got to.
No other choice.
- Where are we gonna go?
Every place has been destroyed.
- I know a place we can go to.
We'll be safe.
- What are we supposed to take?
- Nothing, there's no time.
They'll be here any minute.
- All right, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
- Men, let's go!
- God,
please watch over him.
Protect him.
Protect him because he is the
only one that can save us.
Bring him home to me.
- My unfortunate reason
for drinking with you
is because you're
pretty much the last man
I could drink with.
Other than that, other than
the fact that you made this...
- Ouch.
- So, you know,
I kinda have to.
Yeah, so...
- It is worse for me, you know.
You don't understand.
- Oh, it's worse for you?
- I'm thinking,
I'm having a drink
with the last woman
in the world, but um.
You're Mexican.
- Oh, no you didn't.
Why do you keep saying that?
Oh my God!
- You and Nicho
are Mexican, right?
- Yeah.
- You just try to hide it.
- You want to get punched?
Do you want me to call Nicho?
No? No? Yeah?
- No, I don't.
- You are so stupid.
- I'm out, is what I am.
- Yeah?
- I need some.
- Well, too bad.
- It's mine!
- Yeah, okay, well,
if you want it,
why don't you come get and it?
You want to play a game?
- Sure.
- Chicken.
- Okay.
So what are the rules?
- If you want it, you
should come and get it.
- Really?
- Now you're afraid.
- I'm afraid?
- Mhmm.
- Was that the look
of being afraid?
- How tough are you?
You're too far away.
- Okay.
- Is this a better view?
- I've got a bit
more of an idea.
- Yeah?
Does it look like
I'm afraid now?
- You're still too far away.
- Come on, we have to go!
Let's go!
- Okay, I'm coming.
- Lauren, let's go!
- We need the address
of Robert Tinker.
- Who's Robert Tinker and
why do you need his address?
- Stop trying to stall.
Don't do that!
- Hey, listen.
Let me go get the tools, okay?
- You got this?
- Yeah, yeah,
the clock's ticking though.
Hurry up.
- Hey!
Where you going, British?
- You sure you got this?
- Yeah, I got it, I got it.
- They know our names.
They've seen our faces.
Let's do what we have to do.
- I gotta get Jenny.
- She's right there.
- I gotta.
Jenny, stall him for
one minute, okay?
- What?
- Just stall him!
- We gotta go!
- Lauren, they're coming!
- We can't wait for her.
- No, we're not
going without her.
Just give her a minute, okay?
- All right.
Come on, give me
the information.
- All right, all right.
- You said
you were gonna cooperate.
- If I do this,
will you let us go?
- Yes, yes, yes, just come on.
Get on with it.
- Dispatch, this
is 351 to Central.
Do you copy, over?
- Copy, 351.
They still 10-80?
- Negative.
We got a code 7-50.
Need information
on a one Tinker.
First name Robert.
Over.
Copy code 7-50.
351, standby.
I got a Tinker, Robert.
Address, 219 Monopoly Rd,
Western Country, over.
- Thanks Central, over and out.
- What's the definition
of code 7-50?
Sit down!
I swear to God,
I'm gonna shut you.
- All right.
- What's the definition
of police code 7-50?
- Police code
7-50, officer in duress.
- Officer in duress?
Officer in duress?!
What is this?
- Like I said, we just
wanna go home alive, okay?
- You shouldn't have done that.
- Hey!
- You shouldn't have done that!
- Take it easy, take it easy!
Come on, man!
I'm sorry!
Come on!
Oh my God!
Oh, man.
- So when did it happen?
- Some time today, sir.
- This whole situation's
out of hand already.
- This is important,
Mr. President.
- I don't need you
to remind me of that.
- Yes, sir.
- You tell the Speaker
that he can use
whatever means necessary
to find out who broke
into the apartment
and killed this man.
- With all due respect, sir,
could you be a little more
specific as to our intent?
- When I say, "whatever
means necessary,"
that's exactly what I mean.
Whatever means necessary.
You follow?
- Yes, sir.
With your permission, I'll
tend to it immediately.
- Go for it.
- Copy.
- There's only two of them.
- Should we go around?
- Give me the gun.
- They can't even see us.
- Now's not the time for
a bleeding heart, Lauren.
Now step back.
- Draw attention...
- I said, step back!
Don't you ever do that again!
If it wasn't for me,
we'd all be dead by now.
- They're human,
just like you and me.
- You either live or die.
It's time to pick a side.
This is what we have
to do to survive.
That's the trouble
with people like you.
Never wanna understand anything.
Never want blood on your hands.
- Travis, she's
scared, all right?
Like the rest of us.
She's afraid she's gonna
lose everything she loves.
- I already lost
everyone I already loved.
- Well then you
know how she feels.
- It's good to be home.
Good to be home.
- We'll need food as well.
What the hell is
all this, Travis?
And where's your dad?
- He didn't make it.
This is what he
wanted us to find.
- Who are they?
- They'll get us what
we need to win this war.
- So they're guests.
- Sure.
- Just stay on their good
side, whatever you do.
- Are you sure
about what you're telling me?
- Quite sure, Mr. President.
- I think the priority is to
find out about this machine.
If it can do anything
close to what you say,
it could alter the
course of history.
- In more ways than one.
- So may I inquire as to whether
you had any prior knowledge
of these experiments.
- Of course not, how could I?
We need to get together
a bunch of scientists,
the best in the country.
The best technicians who know
about this sort of thing.
- Yes, sir.
- Figure out how they built it,
what they're gonna do with it.
I need regular updates.
You can't talk to
anybody about it.
- Yes.
- Gotta keep the whole
thing top secret.
- Understood, Mr. President.
Thank you, sir.
- Thank you.
And you,
watch that tongue of yours.
- My apologies, sir.
- I just wonder,
is it possible
what happened to Jack
are these same men
could be responsible
for what happened?
- Sector
Six Control to BioHawk One.
Come in, over.
BioHawk One, receiving.
- BioHawk One,
transport Commander
Dane directly to
the coordinates in Sector Nine,
found to contain
temporal disturbance.
Commander Rankin's strike
team have come under attack
from suspected rebels.
Other units are in route
and will rendezvous
with you at the target.
- Copy that, Control.
Rerouting to target
coordinates, over.
- Check all the rooms.
- What the
hell took so long, huh?
Nicho, Jesus Christ!
There's two more people
that know what we look like
and they're cops!
- We got bigger
things to worry about.
They used a duress code.
- Did you get the address?
- Yeah, I got it but
I just can't trust it.
They could've gave us a
false one, I don't know.
- They don't need to give
us a false address, do they?
They just give us the real
address but wait outside it
then we'll show up and
they'll arrest us there.
- We gotta be careful.
Stay under the radar.
- Yes we do.
- Hey, what're you doing?
- Staying under the radar.
Right?
We can't go to
that house anyway.
They'll be waiting for us.
Hiding in plain sight, mate.
- Everybody out.
- What did you find, Commander?
- We're too late.
- What have we here?
Which one is he in?
- This one.
- That's him.
- I know.
- I spoke to him once, briefly.
I thought I would
never see him again.
- I wanna get a finger print
scan just to make sure.
- It's him.
- This one's got Philip in it.
The last communication
confirms that he successfully
teleported himself back to 2017.
- Really?
Doesn't seem that
successful to me.
They're all dead.
- The soldiers that were
supposed to go with them
were ambushed by
a group of rebels.
- So these machines
can transport a man
back in time.
- He must've been
trying to learn all
the secrets of the machine
from these two beforehand.
- Perhaps another BioCorp
soldier was murdered.
Yes, Commander?
- Yes, sir.
- Get on it.
- Clear the building.
- Commander,
I want a team of our best
scientists, on the double.
I want them to
analyze, to cipher
and duplicate these machines
as soon as possible.
We have to get them working.
- Yes, sir.
- Such power.
Such promise.
The possibilities.
- Get down on
the ground right now!
Put your face on the ground now!
- You don't have to do this.
- Spare us.
We have nothing to
do with you people.
- Please, no, you
don't have to do this.
- Darling, look at me.
Look into my eyes.
It's okay.
We're together.
You'll always be my daughter.
- Kill 'em.
Leave no survivors.
- No, no, no, please don't!
- This elevator is
nicer than our apartment.
- It's true.
At least we had
to live like this.
- It's clean.
- Smells good.
- Jenny would love this, right?
- Yeah, Jenny would love this.
- You ever think about that?
You know,
just moving here?
Starting again,
making a new life.
People have so much here.
Kill ourselves for
what they throw away.
- Yeah.
Where would we go though?
- Anywhere.
- Just forget about this life?
Pretend the future
never happens.
- No.
I know it happens.
Maybe nothing can
stop it happening
but we could be like
better prepared.
Better placed.
Hey, we'd be rich if we stayed.
You think about that?
- We could go to South Africa.
- Now you're talking.
Couldn't get there for
love or money in our time.
- No.
But I got a good memory.
- Me too.
- There's two names that
would always ring on my brain.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Well, what do you say?
We make a break for it?
- Go to Mexico?
- Oh.
No.
Robert Tinker.
We've got a job to do, right?
- I'm game if you are.
- Everything just feels
so impossible now.
- What's impossible?
- I know we couldn't
have stayed but
I just feel awful
leaving him there.
- That,
that was just a shell.
That wasn't Nicho anymore.
- Well it looked
like Nicho to me.
- Don't do this to
yourself, all right?
Your torturing yourself and
it's not gonna help anybody.
- I can only imagine what
they're doing to them.
- We're gonna get them
back, Jenny, I promise you.
- Probably treating
them like lab rats.
- Listen to me,
Nicho's body and soul
are alive and well in 2017.
I saw it with my own eyes.
- Yeah, you saw it, it's
easy for you to say.
I didn't even get
to say goodbye.
When we first met,
he told me that I would be
the one to have his children.
It was like one of
the very first things
that he ever said to me.
It's crazy, isn't it?
- Pick out any names?
- It's just not fair.
- It's why he's back
there, you know?
To fix all this so
you can pick names.
- And if he dies?
- You gotta see this.
- Come on.
- We found this.
- Hey guys.
Jenny,
We're alive.
The connection is severed.
- Where did you get this?
- We found it in his dad's place
with today's date written on it.
We think we left it for us.
- We're in short
supply here in 2017.
Now, guys, this
safe box contains
blueprints to the
machine design.
It's everything you'll need.
Now listen carefully.
The safe box has an
acidic substance,
so if it's forced open,
the vile will break
and data will be lost.
Jenny, this is for you.
Only you know where the key is.
I love you.
I can only trust you.
- This is it.
- There's no more
of the message?
- No.
- No, that's all we ever got.
Where is this key?
- I have no idea.
- You must know
something about it!
Otherwise, why would he
mention it in the first place?
- I don't have a key!
- She's not hiding
anything from you.
- I'm not accusing
her of treason, David,
but if you know something
that you're not telling us.
- If I knew anything,
I would tell you.
- Fine!
There's a combination
lock here too.
So I want you to write
down any and all numbers
significant to you and Nicholai.
Birthdays, anniversaries,
the day you met, when
you fell in love,
the first time you
screwed, everything
and start doing it now!
- What're you gonna do with it?
- We can send a team back
to help Nicholai and Thomas
finish what they started.
- How do you
know it's gonna work?
- Because all of
you are gonna help
in every step of the way.
Not only will we have the
power to save humanity,
but we a alter it for
the good of all of us.
We can defeat BioCorp
before it's ever born.
- Yeah!
- Are you with me?!
Jenny, not is the time to act.
To help save humanity.
Will you do it?
- Yeah, I'll help you.
I'll do whatever it takes.
- Good, Jenny.
You're doing the right thing.
- I can't see you but
I know you're there.
- I never left you.
I'm always with you.
Baby, you need to
leave this place.
You're not safe.
- Oh my God, there's
a cop, there's a cop.
No, no, no, no.
Look, killing people
isn't always the answer.
- This time.
Nicho,
it's not the answer this time.
They're not going away.
Come on.
- David, we have a problem.
- Yeah, I'm ahead of you there.
He's a tad aggressive.
But we've got a common goal.
That should protect us for now.
- What happens when we
don't have a common goal?
- We still need to find a
place to rebuild the machine.
- Wait.
Are you planning to escape?
- There's way to many
people around here.
We couldn't slop off.
So how is it you still have
so many of those things?
- I bought them in bulk
when the economy went down.
- You know, they're still
not exactly good for you.
- Yeah,
well you know what?
I promise I will quit as
soon as I get pregnant.
- Do not make those
jokes around Jenny.
- May I?
- Sure.
- You know, it's
been a long time
since I've seen
a beautiful lady.
Very long time.
You got a guy at all?
- I sure do.
- Lucky guy.
- Isn't he just?
- We didn't have an
appointment proper
but I'm so glad
you could join us.
- Robert Tinker.
What's up, buddy?
We know everything about you.
Every employee,
every friend,
every family member in history.
We know so much about you.
We could strike at any time,
any place,
anywhere.
- It doesn't have to be
like that though, Robert.
You can save them.
All of them.
- Just tell me what
it is you guys want.
- Abandon your ID chip
program research immediately.
- What chip ID project research?
- Don't do that, we
know you're working on it.
- No, I am not
working on anything.
- If you lie to us, Robert,
your family will die.
- Listen to me.
- Do you want...
- Listen to me!
We work on all
kinds of projects,
all the time, simultaneously,
one after the other!
All the time!
None of them have anything to
do with some sort of a chip.
I swear to God I have no idea
what you guys are talking about.
- Then you haven't
created it yet.
- Created what?
What's this thing
supposed to do?
- Show him.
- You see this?
This is what they did to me.
Everyone.
- I've never seen anything
like that in my life.
I mean,
that almost looks
like it's from...
- The future.
- That's because it is
and so are we.
- Oh my God.
Oh my God, time travel?
- Correct.
- How?
How does it work?
I mean, tell me how it works.
- No, we're not
here for that today.
- But if you guys are
here then there has to be,
I don't know, some
sort of problem
with my future or
something, right?
- This chip was
manufactured by your company
and surgically
implanted into every
man,
woman
and child
causing infertility
to the whole race.
- The whole race, as in
the whole human race?
- Yeah.
- Everywhere?
Even like Britain and...
- There are no countries
where we're from, Robert.
Your company made that happen.
The world is a very
different place.
- My corporation...
- Yeah, your corporation.
You sold your corporation
to the government for billions
of dollars, you know why?
They wanted to track
every human being
and your chip,
your chip was the solution.
- Where we're from, Robert,
you're a very hated man.
Very hated but very rich.
- You see, I would never be
apart of a project like that.
I got into this
deal to help people.
- That's what everybody
says before billions
roll into their account!
And all of a sudden
your conscience gets,
poof, into the wind.
- You know the
humiliating part of this?
Huh? Huh?
Do you know?
You.
You get murdered and they
take over your company
and in a few years time,
there is no one
left alive on Earth
because of Robert Tinker.
- If it isn't you, Robert,
then it's somebody who
works for your company.
- So do you know what
needs to happen now?
- I can find out.
I swear to you guys,
I have no idea what
you're talking about but
I allow a lot of my engineers,
my best and brightest,
to exercise their
brilliant creativity.
I allow them to work
on different projects.
My director of special programs,
he oversees everything.
He will know exactly what is
going on, I will ask him...
- What's his name?
- Brandon.
- Brandon what?
- Davidson.
Brandon takes care
of everything.
And Brandon will know.
He'll know exactly
who's doing what
and I will find out,
I will shut it down.
I'll forbade it
within my company.
I will fire the individual.
I can stop this.
I can stop this from happening.
To that, you have to believe me.
I swear to you I can do this.
- You think he's
telling the truth?
- I think if he's lying,
we'll see him again.
You understand that?
- I do.
I do.
- Otherwise,
we're gonna have to erase you.
From history.
- I understand that.
I understand, I got it.
I got it.
- Tell you the truth, Robert.
Nobody in this room ever
wants to see you again.
Ever.
- You won't.
- Because if we do,
there's only one
other way to do this.
- No, no, no, wait, wait,
wait, for God sakes!
I don't know!
I don't want to be an evil man!
I never wanted to do
anything to hurt anybody!
I wanted to help people!
If they're gonna kill me
anyway, why would I do it?
Why would I take the money
if they're gonna kill me?
- Let's go.
Don't worry, buddy.
Call the cops to untie
you when we're clear.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
The time travel, I
really gotta know.
How's it work?
- No.
- Thank you, God.
- Here's everything I know.
- You certain it's everything?
- I'm positive.
There's a few things that are
personal, outside of the wall.
- There's nothing
beyond the wall.
Oh, and I wanna apologize
to you for my behavior.
- Travis, it's fine.
I know, your father and all.
- Thanks, Jenny.
- I don't know about you
but I am exhausted
from all the running.
- All exhausted.
We've been running
away for two days.
- Hey.
Come closer.
- What for?
- Just come closer, I don't
want anyone to overhear.
- What?
- I know the combination.
- You do?
- I didn't give it to them.
- Buying time?
- I'm just running.
- Hey, think you
could do us a favor?
Find us something to eat?
- Please, we haven't ate
or drank anything all day.
- Let me see what I can do.
How would you like
your steak cooked?
- However.
Appreciate it.
- Hey,
Nicho told me to always
trust my instincts.
- Your secret's safe with me.
Whatever is eating at Travis
is gonna drive him to the
wrong decision sooner or later.
- What makes you say that?
- Because the ends
justify the means.
That's how he operates.
- Temptation will
be too much for him.
- So, what do we do?
- Nicho's over there
fighting for us.
We have to do whatever
we can to protect them.
We can't let those
thugs back there.
The design on the
machine dies with us.
- Okay.
- No, I'm serious.
Not your life, not my
life, not Lauren's.
No one's is more important
than what those guys
are trying to do.
- All right.
I'm with you.
Whatever that means.
- Do you know how to
rebuild the machine
without whatever's in that safe?
- I could start it, I
couldn't complete it.
I need Nicho or Thomas
to fill in the gaps.
- No, if we can't do
it, then no one can.
- We probably shouldn't
stay here too long.
If you just have them
a bunch of combinations
that won't work.
- Right.
All right.
Quiet exit.
While they're all asleep.
- I'll tell Lauren.
- I'm sorry.
I just dropped by to
apologize for my behavior.
It was wrong of me.
- You don't say.
- I don't mean to be so abrupt.
I'm just so passionate at times,
it ends out coming
out wrong at times.
- Look,
today was a rough day.
You lost your father.
Nicho always said, things seem
better in the morning, so,
why don't you get
yourself some sleep?
- I'll have my men get
you something to eat.
- That'd be nice.
- Have a shot.
- I'm fine.
- Trust me, Lauren,
you need this more than ever.
- I hope your
father's proud of you.
So,
how's that combination
coming along?
- Nothing yet but
we'll figure it out.
My men are putting together
every possible combination
and testing them out right now.
- Good.
- What can I do for you?
- Just checking to see if
Lauren was good for the night.
You guys need anything
to eat or drink?
- She's got a drink
here, with me.
You get yourself to bed.
There's a good boy.
- Lauren?
- I'm fine.
I'll see you in the morning.
- Something else?
- Have a goodnight.
- That was rude, right?
Can't he see that I'm trying
to chat with a gorgeous girl?
- At least he's trying
to look out for me,
like my brother
Nicho asked him to.
- You all in love with David?
- No.
- Were you ever in love?
- Yes.
- Who's the lucky guy?
You don't talk a lot.
I hope you talk to him.
- When I can.
- Did you tell
him you loved him?
- Yes.
I'm just not sure
if he heard me.
Jenny, stall them
for one minute, okay?
Just stall them!
- We gotta go!
- I love you.
- Damn shame, ain't it?
- Yeah.
- There's nothing
lucky about being dead.
Thomas, right?
- How long do
you think it'll take you
to figure out how
these things work?
- Give it three hours and
we'll have a test to fix it.
- Good.
We're ready to commence
animal trial, sir.
- We don't have time for that.
- You don't want tests?
- Not with animals.
- Might not be safe, sir.
These are like microwaves.
- This microwave
will save our future.
Sacrificing these soldiers
for BioCorp trumps safety.
These are true heroes.
- Sir, we don't even know
how the machines work.
- Time waits for no man.
Get in, get dirty.
This is the only
way to understand
this marvelous gift
we've been given.
- I'll start drafting
volunteers immediately.
We have an opportunity
to do a great service
for the company, the
world and all of mankind
but I need volunteers.
Your mission
will be to hunt down
by any means necessary
the two men
and the two women
who are not only traders
but threaten our very existence.
Bring them to me.