- In the year
2037 our world is dying.
Mankind has been struck by
an infertility pandemic.
Those who suffer childbirth
are rewarded with
a mere 15 seconds of
their baby's life.
Before the virus takes them.
Anyone that does this once,
never attempts it again.
The pain is just too much.
- Today, Biocorp made
made world history
by administering
the cure for cancer.
Available to the entire
world's population,
in exchange for their
voluntary enrollment
in the ID chip program.
- Not a single child
exists in our world today.
Empty schools and empty playgrounds
haunt our waking dreams.
People rioted.
Killed each other in the
hopeless void that faced us.
Biocorp was allowed
to declare martial law
to keep the peace.
Which only meant they
employed hired thugs
to put down anyone
that blamed them
for their futile existence.
An uprising killed 15
million people in 2023.
There hasn't been
a rebellion since.
And what would be the point?
Biocorp doesn't have to care.
No one does.
But it was our fault, really.
Biocorp tempted every human
into accepting the
ID chip program.
A microchip that would cure
every disease known to man.
The promise was immortality.
It almost lived
up to its promise.
We're healthy.
There's no disease in our time.
But there's also no children.
As the chip couldn't
tell the difference
between disease and a pregnancy.
It was tough to put
a brave face on it.
But we had to.
For those we loved.
- Hey, sis.
- Hey, baby.
I found a new place today.
- Oh yeah, how was it?
- Oh, it was great.
- That's good.
- Surprises.
- Surprises?
- Mmm hmm.
- Okay.
- Yup, I did.
Look at this.
- What is that?
What are you trying to
sweeten me up for?
- No, it's not, I
love that smile.
- There's no food is there?
- No, but there's copper wire.
- Oh, copper wire.
- Mm hmm.
- I'm sure that will
taste very delicious.
- Indeed it will, once you put
that secret sauce of yours.
- Oh, a secret sauce of mine.
Hey babe, the secret?
It's out.
- We are on the
verge of finding you.
Believe me our
species will prevail.
You need not worry about that.
- We've heard this before!
Biocorp needs to give
us a solution now!
You made the problem
you should clean it up!
- Sir, we have the best
scientists on this planet.
And we are aware of everything
you are saying, sir.
As I was saying.
Biocorp is protecting
your future.
- Are you trying to
get us both killed?
- They are lying
to us every month!
They're hiding
something in there!
- Of course they are!
- Okay.
- Vanish.
Do you know,
it's people like you.
Scientists.
That ruin our world.
Meddling into things you couldn't
possibly ever understand.
- I understand.
- No you don't.
Our species is dying, that
much you might understand.
What you don't understand
is that our only hope,
lies with the Biocorp
scientists finding a cure
for this pandemic.
And in order for them
to do that, we need to
give them everything they need.
Including cooperation.
Cooperation so they can do their
job as quickly as possible.
- Is that a joke?
Biocorp.
Do you believe
half of the rubbish
you spout from that
podium every month?
Biocorp isn't doing anything.
Biocorp doesn't have a cure.
That's the truth.
Biocorp isn't even
working on a cure.
That's the truth!
You know why?
Because if they were, you'd
be flanked by scientists.
And not guys with guns.
- Wanna cause a panic?
Hmm?
Want the riots again of 2023,
is that what you'd like?
- I want the truth.
- Oh, you want the truth.
Well,
I'm gonna tell you the truth.
And after I tell you the truth,
that man is going to kill you.
So here's the truth.
We've got nothing.
If you'll excuse me, I
have to meet with our CEO.
Make it discreet.
- Perhaps I've got
time for a cigarette.
What do you say?
Thank you.
I know it's not easy.
Just following orders, huh?
You old enough to remember
a time when everyone
was worried about these
things killin' us?
And Biocorp broke in and saved
the world by curing cancer.
Something kinda
funny about that.
Cure every disease.
Including that
horrible one pregnancy.
I haven't got a lighter.
- Alright, ready?
Ready to fly?
- Is everything okay?
- Hey.
- Hi.
- I was skipping curfew.
- Yeah, well maybe
you need a new watch.
Because you've got 30 minutes.
- Right, yeah.
Well maybe I was
rushing home to see you.
- Sister.
Brother's in the room, you know.
- Maybe you should tell me
your brother's still here.
Any joy?
- Uh, if by any joy you mean
putting him into a coma, yes.
By teleporting him 10 feet now.
- We gotta stop killing mice.
I don't feel good about it.
- Yeah, me too.
- Okay.
Tell me about the signal, c'mon.
- Well, it's the same 23
hour 56 minute repetition.
- Okay.
- But there's no way to
track where it's coming from.
- What about the
triangulation by the numbers,
I thought it was something.
- That's just it.
There is a source reading.
If you look right here,
- What did it say?
- Well, it says it's
coming from here.
- Here the apartment?
- Thing has a bug in it.
- We have to
recalibrate it again.
- Yeah.
- Guys, come on
it's getting cold.
- We'll get there with it, mate.
- What did you say?
- Okay, dude, we'll get
there with it mate.
- Don't take the mick outta me.
Damn, mate, just the love tags.
- Hey, easy man.
- It's my turn, it's my turn.
- My turn!
- See what I grew up with?
- Shut up, okay.
Pretend like I never heard
anything you guys said before,
and tell me again, how exactly
is this gonna make us rich?
- Hey, what he's
trying to say is,
that teleportation is possible,
and we actually
have the prototype
- to show to the government.
- A prototype?
- Yes we have the prototype.
- You call that a prototype?
- Okay.
- Yes.
- We'll just stay with
the governor's committee,
and we need more funding so
we can get to the next level.
- Ah, that doesn't work.
- Excuse me, it works.
- It does?
- Yes.
- It was sort of...
- No, phase one of it was.
- Oh, how many phases
- There's like,
two or three phases.
But phase one?
Human mapping.
Encoding.
We can do all of that, we
just can't send it anywhere
cuz it's too big
- Ohhh so you can't really
- teleport anyone.
- It's a little bit...
- Sounds like a little flaw.
- It's not a flaw.
- Just a little bit.
- Actually no, no.
The mapping process
is really impressive.
And the recoding thing
that we figured out
is really cool
- Oh the recoding.
- Oh there he goes
abusing the word cool!
Don't abuse the word cool.
- Once we get the, you know what
once we get the copper
wire around the coils,
all we're going to have to
look at is signal degradation.
- Signal degradation,
that's another magical.
- No, that's something else.
Shut up, sis.
- The signal, mate, you
wanna hear about that?
- I definitely wanna
hear about that.
- Go ahead tell me.
- If you're not worthy
of this story, just say, okay?
- Tell it.
- Go ahead, sis.
- Every day for the last
year, every 23 hours,
56 minutes, we get a signal
that lasts six seconds.
- What does it say?
- Well, it's more like a beacon.
- Oh, a beacon.
- No, but...
- I was thinking,
- So who's sending it?
- Where is it coming from?
- We're beaconing you.
- Yes, but it's on
the top of our list,
we're figuring it out.
- Oh, I have a few things
for the top of the list.
- Okay, okay, you know what?
You know what?
Why don't you guys just
let us know sometime.
- You know if you
guys wanna chip in...
- Hey.
- You on lookout duty?
- No, just came up
for a breath of fresh air.
- Ah.
You okay?
You seem a little off.
- I haven't come up
to the roof everyday
to think about things.
- What were you thinking about?
- I was thinking,
it is going to rain.
- You know that's really
a British stereotype,
talking about the weather?
- Okay, am I living
up to that right now?
- You are living up to it.
- Right.
- Uh huh.
- Well, I don't know if
you'd be really interested
in what I was really
thinking about anyway.
- Yeah the fact that you were
thinking is what's impressive.
But go on.
- Okay, well you'll like this
one slightly better then.
- Okay, okay.
- I was thinking about you.
- You were thinking about me?
That's nice.
- Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
- Hey, you okay?
- I don't want you to, uh,
pin all your hopes on me.
Not me.
And you know what I am for you?
I'm a lack of options.
I'm a distinct lack of options.
- Why don't you
stop talking, okay?
Look, I don't know what's
going on with you, but,
don't try and push me
away with this crap
and not tell me what's
really going on, okay?
So what's going on?
- We can't, we can't.
- You can't.
- I feel like
something's coming.
And I might not always
able to be here.
- Okay.
- Where would we go?
- Where would we go,
there's nowhere to go.
There's nothing
beyond the city walls.
Not anymore.
Here is all we got.
- Is here that bad?
- No here's, pretty
wonderful sometimes.
But you know here is
also owned by Biocorp.
Biocorp, who can turn
up whenever they want,
take whatever they want simply
because it pleases them.
And that's a
precarious place to be.
- We're safe here.
Together.
- Yeah.
Did you feel that?
That was a raindrop.
- Why are you changing
- That's a raindrop!
- The subject?
- I'm not changing
- I get with the rain.
- I'm standing up here to
- You are gonna,
- That's a raindrop.
- I'm gonna kill you
one of these days.
- It is gonna fully rain.
- I've got powers or something.
- I can't even have
a serious conversation
with you, I swear!
You're gonna kill me
one of these days.
Oh boy.
- Our efforts to find a
cure for a disease that has
plagued our generation,
will take longer
than we first predicted.
We've all suffered greatly.
And without ever being
able to bring to justice
whatever disease put
us in this position.
The global biological clock
- Is ticking against us.
At this time,
- during our darkest hour
- During our darkest hour,
as we go through hell,
- As we go through hell,
the only thing we can do,
- The only thing we
can do, is keep going.
- Is keep going.
- That's pretty good.
We can go ahead
and release that.
- It is, with a heavy heart,
that I address you today.
Our efforts to find a cure
for a disease that has
plagued our generation,
will take longer than
we first predicted.
Block 14, report to Sector Nine.
- Can't sleep?
- Uh,
no.
I was just gonna, um...
You?
- Bad dream.
- The one with the kid, right?
- Yeah, nightmares of the
mind are the craziest thing.
Make you believe
things about people
that um,
you never thought
they'd ever do.
- Yeah.
- Hmm.
What's up buddy?
- You know I should, uh,
I think it'd be best if I...
Look, I uh,
I killed a Biocorp guard today.
- What?
- Had no choice, really.
It was like a self defense,
the speaker, he was lying
in the forum, right?
So I called him
out on it, but I,
I didn't know what else to do.
- Where's the body?
The body, where's the body?
- I had to leave him, uh,
It's in an alleyway.
- No you're not,
they're gonna find it.
- No, it's under debris.
It's like on a
- Oh my God.
- Nick, what was
I supposed to do?
What was I supposed
to rollover and die?
- What were you supposed to do?
Thomas what you're supposed
to do is not come here,
after you kill a Biocorp guard!
You know you put my sister
and my wife in harms way?
- I didn't...
- They're gonna find
you, you gotta chip.
An ID chip.
- They won't track me,
here we're in concrete.
I'll be, it'll be muffled.
That's why I went here.
- Oh so you're so
sure about that, huh?
- I'm not sure
- You're not sure about much.
- Sure hey, but,
look it happened so fast.
I was gonna, hey what are
you doing what are you doing?
- Whoa whoa whoa whoa!
- I'm going
to clean up your mess.
Where's the body?
- Please, let me go.
I was gonna go, let me go.
- Where is the body?
- If I go, the
problem goes with me.
Please.
I can't let you go, you can't
go back to the scene of the
crime for Christ's sake,
they'll see you
comin' it's curfew!
- Yes but if we
don't find the body,
they're gonna find you in less
than 24 hours with your chip.
Thomas, where's the body?
Thomas!
- What, what, no wait,
what did you say?
- I said where's the body.
- No no did you say, you
said they'd find me in
- Less than 24 hours
- So what.
- A day, a day, right?
24 hours a day.
- Yeah, so what?
- What's less than 24 hours?
- What are you talking about?
- 23 hours, 56 minutes.
- Yeah.
- 23 hours 56 minutes.
That signal, that comes in
every 23 hours 56 minutes.
- Right, so what?
- You know what else it is?
The exact length of a
rotation of the Earth.
A day.
We just round it up to, to
24 hours for convenience.
- Right?
- Right, I know that.
But what difference does it make
when there's a body out there
that needs to be dealt with?
Otherwise they're gonna
ship us to the outer lands!
- Stop thinking about distance.
Stop thinking
about where we are.
It's about when.
The signal.
When is the signal?
Not where is it coming from,
when is it coming from?
- When?
- It's a day.
Someone wants us to
- When?
- pay attention to time.
- Think about it.
The teleportation
system, we start
working on that a year ago.
Then we start
gettin' this signal.
At the exact same time.
Right?
We're so obsessed with
trying to change one variable
we can't seem to control.
Distance.
But we're forgetting
about the other variable.
What if we hold distance
firm and we change
the only other variable we can?
- The other variable being time.
- Time.
- But how do we...
- How do we?
How'd you did?
The signal,
the beacon it's our beacon.
It's from right here,
right in this room!
It's just not from right now.
- Alright, look.
The frequency of the
signal shifts by a decibel
and then it just resets.
- Okay, but it
shifts and resets.
So look for a pattern.
- I got it.
It's repeating binary code.
- Let's see it.
Let's see it!
What do you got,
what do you got?
- Uh, it's a
sequence of numbers.
Uh, 1-2-2-0-2-0-1-7.
What does it mean,
what does it mean?
- Um, I, location
coordinates for something.
- No no no that's not enough
for longitude latitude.
Uh, it's, ah...
Thomas!
We're idiots!
Look it's not, look!
It's time.
It's a date.
December 20th, 2017.
- My god, that's before Biocorp.
- Exactly!
- Before the virus
became a pandemic.
- I know.
We can go back.
We're almost there.
We can go back and fix all
this before it ever happened.
- Go back?
We can't send Henry 10 feet
without inducing a coma.
- Maybe we didn't.
Check this out, buddy.
Look, come here.
Alright, look.
As long as Henry was in
stasis, his brain activity was
consistent to rodent
that was awake.
It was all because he was awake.
He was alive somewhere
moving around!
- Niko, that's a big assumption.
We don't know if that's
true and even if it is,
it's a one way trip!
We never brought anybody back!
- But if this is right, we're
talking about time travel.
I mean we could fix all this
before it ever happened.
Jesus, Thomas.
We're talking about the
extinction of Mankind!
Don't pretend we have
to think about this.
- Okay, okay you're right.
You're right, okay?
So who gets to go?
- Look, I'll go because
if something happens to me
I need you to take
care of the girls.
- Great, you're going to
leave me explaining this crap?
- Yeah.
- Oh.
I'll go, because I'm the
guy who killed somebody.
- I'm the wanted man.
- No because this was my idea.
- You don't need this sore.
- You know the guy I am.
I'm always trying to
take responsibility.
- You don't need to suffer!
- So let me handle
the consequences.
Isn't that what
you want me to do?
- We're gonna flip for it.
- We're not gonna flip for it.
- Yes we are.
- We're gonna flip for it.
- No, I'm gonna go.
- No, this is gonna happen.
Otherwise I'm kicking your ass.
- Fine, flip.
- Heads.
- Best of three.
- Shut up and help
me get this going.
- His name is Thomas.
He's an enemy of the state.
He murdered a Biocorp employee.
This is your new target.
We need swift justice.
Set an example.
To everybody in Sector Nine.
In a state of emergency,
disobedience will not be tolerated.
Dismissed.
- Okay, okay.
- So, uh, this is it.
- Oh yeah, yeah, yes yes.
- Okay you know and
if anything happens,
you just, you know.
- I know, I know,
I know, I know.
You want me to marry
your sister, right?
- No, no.
I'll be back to make
sure that doesn't happen.
Ah.
- Assuming this works,
how am I gonna know it works?
- I'm gonna use this beacon
to send us a little blip.
- That answers that question.
Now, what would you like
me to say to your wife?
- Tell her,
Tell her I love her.
I'm doing this for the child
that we never got to have.
- That sounds, terrible.
I'm going to make up something
much better later on ok?
Much more classy.
Then I'll deliver it
in my British accent,
and she'll love it, your
sister will love it,
- it's comforting.
- I get it.
- You know what I'm saying.
- Mm hmm.
- So this is gonna work?
What are you gonna do
when you get there?
- Tell the people what's coming.
- That's a little vague,
you'll look like a madman.
- Tell President Williams.
- And how you gonna
find President Williams?
- I don't know.
What university did President
Williams attend in 2017?
- President
Jack Williams lectured at
Chesterfield University
between 2013 and 2018.
- Think ahead, buddy.
- I've always got my answers.
Get in the coffin.
I can tell you this
stings by the way.
Hey mate?
Good luck.
- You're the one that
has to tell the girls.
- Very true.
Okay.
Adam, start the bio scan.
- Bio scan initiated.
- Alright, mate.
This'll put you to sleep.
Adam is the system ready?
- Bio scan complete, Thomas.
System ready.
- Alright.
Here we go.
Adam,
hit it!
- Time displacement
program initiated.
- What the hell is going on?
- Jesus, you scared
the heck out of me.
- Thomas, what the
hell is going on?
- He didn't tell you about this?
- Don't talk, talk to me.
- Okay, whoa whoa,
release, okay.
We found something.
- It's Biocorp.
- Oh God.
I have to go.
- What?
- I have to go.
What the hell are
you talking about?
- I have to lead
them away from us.
- What am I supposed to do?
- You don't need to
do anything, okay
the machine will run itself.
Okay, let me, if you
need to wake him,
- you use the adrenaline.
- Adrenaline, what?
- I thought you couldn't
wake anyone in stasis.
- Ah.
- Better not be true.
- Why do I have a funny feeling
I might be safer outside?
- Because you might.
Look, just wake him
up and we can go.
Wherever the hell you wanna go.
- Look, I can't, okay?
- What do you mean?
- Because I don't know how.
- What?
- Niko got in that machine
as a leap of faith.
Okay, he's doing it to save us.
All of us.
- They say you killed a trooper.
- Yeah, okay.
- What?
- They're here!
- How many?
- Whole platoon!
They've surrounded the building.
What's happening?
- Yeah, what is happening?
- Okay, let me explain
the most important thing
right now for us all is to
keep them out of this building.
- Okay, okay how do we do that?
- I don't know.
- Do we have any weapons?
- No.
- Ooh, oh what
abut the failsafe?
- No, is it even armed?
- I can arm it!
- No no no no no!
You'll kill the power.
- Okay, okay.
We need to stop them.
- If you kill the
power, you kill Niko.
- What do
we know about this place?
- Five floors, 25
citizens, all legal.
- Armed?
- We have to presume so, sir.
- Show me.
- Best breach points
are here, and here,
north and south walls.
- Can I leave this with you?
- Sure.
Thank you sir.
- Make it clean, Edier.
- Yes, sir.
- Everyone listen!
We've got a cure
for the pandemic,
but Biocorp are here
trying to steal it!
Protect this building and
I'll give you the cure!
- That's how he wants to play.
- You heard the man!
Look around and find yourself
something to use for a weapon!
- Take your assault positions.
- Sir!
- Well, that brings
up the eternal debate.
Would you kill Adolf Hitler?
Would you go back in time,
and end his life as a baby?
Okay, one at a
time, one at a time.
- Jeremy.
- Of course I'd
kill him as a baby.
I'd even murder his parents,
so they couldn't
create another monster.
- Well, who agrees
with that answer?
Michelle?
- Uh, um...
- I wouldn't want
to change past.
If not Hitler, it would
have been someone else.
It could have been
someone worse.
- Okay.
See, most of the world's
problems can be avoided,
if we lost the human
desire to meddle.
We're meddlesome.
And we shouldn't be.
Okay, that's it.
Guys read chapter
seven and eight,
might be a quiz next Friday.
Have a good night.
- Jack?
- Yes?
- Hey.
I'm a friend of your fathers.
Um, I was thinking about
throwing a party for him.
Seeing if you can,
give me a hand.
- You know, talk to my
brother about that stuff.
He's better and he's always
wanting to make daddy happy.
- No no no, see, uh, I need you.
You're, you're the guy I need.
- Okay well I, uh, teach
class in 30 minutes.
So time's not
really on our side.
- Very true.
- Find substation access
panel one three H.
Cut the feed.
Let's make 'em sweat in there.
- Yes sir.
- The power is in your hands.
- So, let me get this straight.
Firstly, you don't know my dad.
Secondly, I'm going to become
the President of
the United States,
and thirdly, be responsible
for the demise of the planet.
So you traveled back in time,
to warn me.
- Yes, look.
Jack.
You have the power to save
the entire human race.
Jack.
There's no kids left in 2037.
- Are you high right now?
- No, Jack I'm not high.
Look I know this sounds crazy
- Look it's been a pleasure
speaking with you, but I have
to prepare for mid terms.
- Please.
- No, I don't have
time for this.
- Look, look.
Listen to me.
I will do whatever it takes,
to save the entire world
from your bad decisions.
- You know what
this isn't right.
And you need help.
Okay.
- Sit down, jack.
- He's connected to
the box in stasis,
but his brain activity
is like he's awake.
- So it's looks like
he's walkin' around.
- Power cell breach.
Thomas.
System inline initiating.
- Oh bullocks.
Must hurry.
- What, what's happening?
- They're accessing
the local power grid.
We need to wake him up.
- What do you mean?
- What's going on?
- Biocorp outside are
accessing the local power grid.
- That can only mean one thing.
- They're about to cut
the power for the building
before they storm in here.
- That'll cut the life support.
- Hence, we need to wake him up.
- Well, what about
a backup generator?
- That would buy us
time, hours only.
It doesn't fix the problem.
What we need to do is wake
him up so we can move him.
So I need a massive dose
of adrenaline to do that.
David, please get it for me!
David, please!
- Okay.
Is it safe?
- He can handle it.
Do it.
- Have you ever done
anything like this?
- Many times.
On mice.
- And how are they doing?
- Alright here we go.
- Alright c'mon let's do this.
- What the hell is going, help!
Hey somebody help!
- Turn it off now!
- Stop it!
- It's out!
- Okay we need to flush
out the adrenaline.
He needs another IV line.
- A new IV line.
- Flush out the adrenaline.
- Right, okay, yeah.
Right.
- I'm sorry.
- You're sorry?
- What the hell's going on?
- What happened?
- You must be an
epileptic or something.
Please, untie me and let me
take you to the hospital!
- No, no, I just...
There's no way to,
we don't have time for that.
- How's he doing?
- Well, his
pressure's decreasing.
He'll be okay.
- He'll be okay?
- Jenny.
- He'll be okay.
Okay mister genius,
why don't you tell me,
why didn't it work?
- Because we've never
tried it before.
- What?
- Jenny, we don't have
any ideas here, okay?
- Look, this is
uncharted territory.
We're figuring it out as we go.
Alright, we're tired, we're
under pressure, we need to
- Sleep.
- Sleep, we need
- No, no no no.
- Not us, we need hm to sleep.
- Now keep going.
- Brain activity.
What does it look
like on the monitor?
- It's like he's walking
around in the past.
- Okay, but he
couldn't make the trip
unless he was unconscious.
- So, maybe, if he were
unconscious in the past,
- He could make the trip home.
- Do it.
- Back up system engaged.
Please find an
alternative power source
- We don't have a lot
of time to tell him.
- To avert system failure.
- You know what,
here's a bright idea.
You sent him, you
bring him home.
- Must be something
wrong with the system.
We don't have time.
- What system, what
are you talking about?
- About you
destroying the world,
that's what we're talking about.
- Look, unfortunately, I
don't have time for this.
Okay?
- You,
you're gonna listen to
everything I have to say.
You and your father commission
a company called Biocorp.
- In 2037.
- Before then.
- You're not
epileptic, you're just crazy.
- Look, I didn't come
all this way for nothing.
- All the way from the future?
- Yes!
- 2037!
- Okay, fine!
Go, go ahead, amuse me!
- Amuse you, I'll amuse you.
Where I'm from, the
entire world is ending.
Do you even know
what that feels like?
Can you even comprehend that?
Can you?
- I've never seen
activists work like you!
Who is it you work for?
Greenpeace?
Or is this because my
father is a Senator?
- Jack, listen!
You're gonna be the
President in the future.
- Listening.
- Yes the President.
And you're going to
ruin the entire future.
Because you don't
have the information.
But, Jack, listen.
I'm trying to give
you the information.
You have to help me.
- You are crazy!
- Everything I'm telling
you is the truth.
- You wanna know the truth?
You have kidnapped, and you have
threatened the life
of a senators son!
- Jack.
- When my father
gets a hold of you,
you are gonna get
the death penalty!
- Yes sir, yes.
I'll notify him immediately.
- What's wrong?
- We need to initiate
protection protocol, Senator.
Your son's been
reported missing.
- The rest of the family?
- Being secured as we speak.
Please follow me.
- So you were gonna leave
without saying goodbye?
- I'm coming home.
- I saw the bags at the door.
You were gonna leave as
soon as you got here.
- I was just trying
to protect you.
You understand that?
I would never, ever hurt you.
You have no idea how
much I care about you.
Okay?
If I hurt you, it
would be a nightmare.
For me.
- You know, for a genius, you
don't know how dumb you are.
- Well you can beat me
up about how stupid I am
when I get home.
- It's a deal.
- I'll come back.
- You sure you wanna do this?
- No, no not really.
But, uh, he'd do
it for me though.
- Thomas.
- You bring back my husband.
- I'll try.
- We're ready for you now.
- Keep it on as
long as possible.
'Cause if we get cut off here,
I have no idea what
happens to us then.
Let's do this.
- They're inside.
- We have to get time.
- Let's go.
- Adam, run the program.
- Where did you come from?
Are you okay?
- I need to save us.
I need to find out where
Chester University campus is.
- It's two blocks that way.
- Thank you.
Yeah.
- Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack.
Listen to me.
I'm going to have to kill you
and your family if you
don't listen to me.
Like...
What the hell?
Thomas.
- We don't have
time to convince.
We can't take that risk.
- Hey.
Hey, it's going to be okay.
- Yeah.
- Thomas are you crazy?
- I'm starting to do something
definitive in this time.
- We had to!
- You can't
go around killing people!
Hey, hey!
I'm here.
It worked, it worked.
It's a time machine.
You guys made a time machine.
Which by the way is way
cooler than teleportation.
- How are the girls?
- Oh, they're freakin' out.
Which is why I'm here.
'Cause, cause we gotta
get you back now.
- No.
We're not leaving 'cause
nothing's changed.
- So how do we know?
- We'd have vanished, right?
We'd have reset in some way.
- What if, what if we're
protected in a temporal bubble?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah or
maybe nothing's changed.
The future is still there
waitin' for us and we gotta go.
- No no, we are not going
home until we know it worked.
Otherwise we made
the trip for nothing.
- Who's the President.
- President?
- The President.
- Who's the President?
- Williams.
- That can't be.
- Why?
- Because Thomas killed him.
- You killed John Williams?
- Yeah, and...
- Wait.
Who's John Williams?
- Did you...
Did you just kill Jack Williams?
- I did what I had to do.
Okay?
So who the hell
is John Williams?
- He's the President.
Who ran for office,
to make the world
a better, safer place
'cause they never caught the guy
who killed his
older brother Jack.
- You have a purpose.
Make your brother proud.
- Yes, sir.
- Every day of your life,
you look in the mirror
and you see your brother in you!
See your mission.
Your purpose.
- Yes, sir.
- Go to your mother.
- So, we changed nuthin'.
- No, wait,
- we changed who was President.
- That was nothing.
- That's something.
- We changed the President.
- What did that
achieve, Thomas?
What did that achieve?
- I don't know.
- We still have a
world that's infertile.
You know, half the
world is dying.
Because the riots of
2023 still ravaged
every hope of us finding a cure!
- You mean 2021.
- What?
- No it doesn't matter.
- No what did you say?
- It might matter.
- No, I get what he's saying.
- What does it matter.
- When was the riots?
- Wait, what do you
mean, what, what year?
- 2021.
- We advanced the
riots by two years.
- How many people died?
- 90 million.
- We've added 40 million
to the death toll.
- What?
- When we left, the riots
of 2023, 50 million people.
We're making things worse.
And quicker.
We can fix it though.
- We can fix this.
- No, no.
We can't do this.
We can't.
- We can fix this.
- No more reaching.
- We were unable to trace them.
- What do you mean?
Find who killed my son.
- Sir, we know that
they're foreign.
Their accent, their clothing.
- Is that all you've been
able to come up with?
- We need a system.
Secure the population.
- Stop thinking and
talking and go find them!
I want those men
that killed my son.
- Yes sir.
- We gotta be clever.
And quick.
Time is not on our side.
- He's right.
Biocorp is still outside
your door in 2037
and they're not exactly
in a forgiving mood.
- Wait, they're alone?
- No they're buying us time.
- And how are they
gonna do that?
- Jenny's gonna
use the failsafe.
- It's going to cut the
power to the machine.
- The machine is
already out of power.
We're on the backup
generators now,
that's why I'm here.
- And what happens
to us if the machine
runs out of power while
we're still plugged in?
♪ Day you called the
sun was big and low ♪
♪ To the ground
♪ The cold had froze
my fingers tight ♪
♪ Time was still and I
was lost from sight ♪
♪ For a while
♪ The call is new
to turn me loose ♪
♪ You had my heart
♪ I knew it from the start
♪ You had my heartbeat
called inside ♪
♪ And every picture made
♪ And every song that played
♪ Is tattoed on
my skin forever ♪
♪ You ain't ever
gonna feel love ♪
♪ You won't ever feel
the way this hurts ♪
♪ 'Cause all the memories
that we dreamed of now ♪
♪ Have all been
washed away do ya ♪
♪ Do you ever wanna feel love
♪ Do you ever feel
the way this hurts ♪
♪ 'Cause all the memories
that we dreamed of now ♪
♪ Have all been washed away