- Previously On Dystopia.
- Well the connections
been severed.
- Abandon your
ID chip program research.
Immediately.
- We need to get together
a bunch of scientists.
The best in the country.
Figure out how they built it,
what they're gonna do with it.
- So these machines
can transport a man
back in time.
- The safe
box contains blueprints
to the machine design.
Everything you'll need.
- I want you to write down any
and all numbers significant
to you and Nicholai.
- I know the combination,
I didn't give it to them.
- You don't want tests?
- Not with the animals.
- Word of advice kid.
Football's on it's way out.
Learn how to shoot a gun.
- I owe you far more
than I can ever repay.
- Perhaps we could pull
in a big favor one day.
- I'm gonna have to
kill you and your family
if you don't listen to me.
- Stop talking and go find him.
I want those men
that killed my son.
- Anything?
- Nope, I've
tried every single number
she gave me and every
single possible combination.
- Okay, she said there's
a key behind the wall.
You still got Ming
out there right?
- Yeah.
- Alright good.
Radio him and tell
him to get moving.
- Go by choice.
- What was that?
- Nothing.
There's got to be a
way to crack this open.
- You've seen the video, it'll
destroy everything inside.
- It's probably a bluff.
- There's only one way in.
That's through the
combination, figure it out.
- She is hiding something.
- Probably.
- I'm not hiding anything.
I've given you every
meaningful number
that I can think of.
- So where's this place?
- In what used to be Vegas.
Here.
Here is the address.
There is a community of
people that are living
outside of Biocorporal.
Peacefully living.
- Sweetheart, crying
is about as much use
as tits on a bull.
- Okay, we'll get
our guy out there.
But it'll take a bit of time.
- Thank you.
- And now
for tonight's top story.
Today Nobel Peace Prize
winning BIOCORP made history
by administering
the cure for cancer.
Available to the entire
world's population
in exchange for their
compulsory enrollment
in the ID chip program.
Which allows for increased
population security.
BIOCORP CEO stated,
"It takes a brave man"
"to knock on the
door of evolution"
"without knowing what
lies on the other side".
"But we've taken the
first brave step"
"to improving our
children's future today".
"Go through the door
and what awaits you"
"on the other side is
something worth fighting for".
Wise words indeed.
And a momentous
day for all of us.
I'm sure you can agree.
- And we're clear.
- There's been another
development sir.
- Well I would imagine it is.
We're not here to
chit chat, what is it?
- Well sir, apparently
the Unity of Lost Children
have their meeting
room scientists.
- I was told they were all dead.
- That report was
erroneous, sir.
Seems they were
rescued by the children
after we took the building.
- We have the building.
- Yes sir.
We have it again.
There was a second assault.
- The Speaker lied to me.
- Perhaps sir, but the
information coming in right now
is just so unclear
that we don't...
- Don't try to cover up for him.
- No sir, I'm just trying
to clarify this situation.
- We need to look at this
as a golden opportunity.
Those rebels have been
a thorn in my side
for a very, very long time.
Unfortunately, launching
an all out assault
upon them has been a very
unpopular distraction.
You tell The Speaker that we
will not tolerate failure.
- Yes sir, immediately.
In here soldier.
- You sure this safe sir?
- It's worked before.
- Good thing sir.
- Remember when you
get to the other side
find them.
- They're very dead sir.
- Not in 2017.
Our scientists have discovered
they are alive and well.
Get as much recon as you can.
- Do you wan them
dead or alive sir?
- Whatever's most expedient.
You'll not only be doing
BIOCORP and mankind a favor,
but the Lord Almighty
is on our side
in this struggle.
It's good versus evil.
- What if I get stuck sir?
- Like them.
- You won't.
They weren't the sharpest tools.
You are trained BIOCORP soldier.
- Yes sir.
- Your time of glory is at hand.
- Here soldier, take this.
Thank you sir.
Let's do it.
- Everybody out.
- Activate.
- Clear.
- Five,
four, three,
two,
one.
- What's wrong?
I have no idea.
- Help me sir.
- Prep it for the next one.
- Maybe
we should use lab animals.
It takes less time.
- It's less...
- Less what?
- Expensive.
- Dead soldiers are free.
Fix it.
Prep for the next one.
- Burn all this.
Send in the next one.
- You know they don't
all believe in it.
- Huh?
- Time travel.
- I do.
- What are you talking about?
- I took your advice, buddy.
I gave up football and
I learned to shoot.
- What, that was you?
- That was what a
few days ago for you?
- Yeah.
- 20 years ago for me.
But I bet I remember
it just as well.
- I remember you
never said thank you.
- Thank you, the world
ended four years later
and you knew it was coming.
Why would I possibly thank you?
- We're gonna get that combo.
Leave me.
- So, how are we
gonna get to the sea
with all these fools around?
- Gotta keep Travis
occupied for one thing.
- And I suppose you
have a plan for that?
- Poison?
- That's a bit extreme,
don't you think?
- I'm not so sure.
- How are we gonna find
poison in this dump?
- Pretty poison?
Okay.
I guess I'll have
to do what it takes.
- We have to protect the future.
- Don't try to make your
idea of me seducing someone
into some sort of
lofty word say.
- Okay.
You gotta get nasty
with him in there
for us to get the
hell outta here.
- Hey, if anything
happens I need to tell you
the nomination.
- Should be some over here.
- That's him.
- Yeah that's him?
- Yeah.
- Are you sure
that's the right guy?
- It's definitely the right guy.
- Alright, let's go.
- Excuse me, sir are
you Professor Howard?
- Yes, I am.
- I'm Nicholai.
- And I'm Thomas.
I'm sorry we're massive fans.
- Nice to meet you gentleman.
- Wow.
- Can't believe it.
It's such a great honor.
Your accomplishments,
everything you wrote here
is amazing.
- Really I'm flattered.
- See we're authors and...
- Right.
- And we wanted to
write a book about you...
- And your genius.
- What about me exactly,
do you want to write about?
May we ride with you
and we'll take a
moment to tell you.
- Right after you sir, come on.
- Please.
- I guess.
- This is so unreal, huh?
- Professor, we'd like
to talk to you about
writing a book
about your research.
Theories on temporal physics.
I've never quite heard
it called that before.
- Well we think
it's the best way
to describe what it is you do.
- Yeah.
- Still doing a research
based book on a researcher
that's very meta.
Oh great.
- Are we stuck?
- I don't know.
- I certainly hope not.
- Call.
- What?
- Hit the call button.
- What's the call?
- Look Professor...
- Perfect.
- The meda, what was
that thing you said
about the meda?
- Meta with a T.
Research on researchers?
- Professor maybe we
could just ask you
a couple of questions you know.
- About me or time travel?
- What we need is your
personal, how should I say?
- Ethical.
- Ethical take on the matter,
you know.
- Look, presently I just
don't have a lot of time
to deal with this.
- That isn't true at all Professor.
- We have loads of time.
So how about we just
ask you a few questions.
We'll jot down some notes,
take it back to the editor.
- Yeah.
- Then come back
with a book proposal.
- Who's your editor?
- Jennifer.
- The good one.
- Good, good one.
- Yeah.
- Is she a science editor?
Because I don't want anybody
who doesn't understand
what I'm talking about
overseeing a book about me
and my work.
- No, no, no, no.
I can assure you
between the two of us
we know enough about
this to do this justice.
- Trust me.
- Yeah.
- So
what kind of deal do we
have on the table here?
- A deal.
- The money gentleman?
- The money.
- This is like a first.
- This is more like a
conversational kinda thing.
And then we're gonna
you know cross the T's,
dot the I's and then boop.
- This is probably a
matter better taken up
with my literary agent
if you wouldn't mind.
- They know the combination.
Watch them closely.
- I hope to teach a class
on time travel someday.
- That would be fantastic.
- Sign us up, right.
- But it's been difficult
to convince administration
it's worth it.
Practicality is the bottom
line order of the day.
There's no such thing as pure
research universities anymore.
- Perhaps our work together
will convince him otherwise.
See that they need
this class, you know.
- That is your best
selling point yet.
- Imagine that time
travel schools.
- Now that would
be something wouldn't it?
'Course you'd probably
have the problem
of the seniors
ditching out on class
once they figured out they
could party in ancient Babylon.
- So professor, tell us.
Are there rules to time travel?
- Ah, now we get
to the fun stuff.
- What I'm trying to say
is can you explain it
in the most practical
application?
- Of course.
Are there rules, well sure.
And they are quite
serious actually.
If you don't follow them
you could end up dead,
lost in time, or the
most frightening of them
you could destroy the future.
- Some people might want
to destroy the future.
So what are these rules exactly?
- Well the first one is the one
that most people
fundamentally misunderstand
and I blame it on
lack of knowledge,
Hollywood, what have you.
Well, here it is.
You cannot
change the past.
No way, no how.
- You cannot, or you should not?
- Can not.
- Why?
Because the Butterfly Effect?
- In a way.
- Okay so.
What you're saying is you
can't even alter the past,
not even a little bit?
- If you change it
even a little bit
you throw everything
else out of whack.
- Well that makes it
sound like you can,
you just shouldn't.
- In a sense it's both.
If you try and change the past,
something in the past,
the future changes.
Therefore what was the past,
ceases to be your past.
- Sounds like an
existential problem to me.
- The problem of one's
existence is very real here,
and not a theoretical
or spiritual plane.
- I don't get it,
I don't understand.
Imagine you had a time
machine that you could use.
Give it some kind of
practical example.
If I were to go
back to yesterday
and force myself to
stay in bed all day.
I have not changed the past.
What I have done in
essence just changed
that specific moment
in that present.
So everything that comes
after that is a new reality
based on that choice.
So if I return to today,
even if my staying in
bed had real, clear,
recognizable consequences
I would only recognize it
as a result of my new present.
You can change the future,
but you can not change
the past.
- Okay, so I get it now.
So in that sense the
future is never new,
but simply your current reality.
- Exactly.
- No, no.
What does that movie tell
us in Back to the Future?
That if we have the technology,
we can go back in time
and we can change things.
And it will effect everything,
past, present, and future.
It's like a documentary
to you people, right?
- Well not really.
It's full of holes and
there's one major difference.
- What's that?
- I've never traveled
through time.
- Professor, we've also
seen that you've written
a lot about temporal distortion.
Can you ad lib on that?
- Yes, it's a key
component of my research.
And one of the primary
tenants of time travel.
Though I'm still trying
to discover the mechanics
of it on a theoretical plane.
- Why only on a
theoretical sense?
- Because unless you know
somebody who's holding out
on me and the rest of the world.
Mechanically it
does not exist yet.
- It doesn't have to exist yet.
It can exist tomorrow.
Isn't that the wonderful
realm of possibility
that we're talking about?
- Professor, does
temporal distortion
allow physical coexistence
on all parts of time?
- Why do you ask?
- Think about it
on two time planes.
Can one body coexist on both
time planes concurrently?
- Where are you getting
these questions from?
- Yeah, you.
- Your research.
You've done so much of it,
it's gone quite in depth.
- And we drew our
own conclusions
about the nature of time.
- But also wanted to learn
about time travel for ourselves.
- It would seem the two
of you know a lot more
about little old moi
than you've let on.
- Our guy's on the way.
He'll get there soon.
- I don't know that
Nico was thinking.
- That's a good question.
- So now what?
- We turn to the past.
- How the machine's
at the apartment.
- We are running out of time.
So I'm gonna give you
one simple command.
Give me the combo.
- I don't know the combination.
I told you.
- I'll tell you what I'd like.
I'd like to defeat BIOCORP
and save the future.
But I'd like help in doing that.
But I don't seem to be
getting help that I need.
In the immortal words of
the great George W. Bush,
"You're either with
us, or against us".
- Which one are you?
- I'm with you.
I'm with you.
- Then give me the combination.
Shooting me is not
going to help you.
- What will?
- Trust.
- Trust?
Put down the gun.
Huh, put it down.
I'm surprised at you.
I'm surprised that you
haven't figured it out.
- I don't know what
he could have meant.
- Oh no, not that.
Stop talking about
him, he's gone.
This is about new
beginnings anyway, right?
You know.
You're so tough.
But underneath it
- I suspect you're kind.
- You don't know me.
- I want to change that.
I bet you're all muscle.
So hard,
- nice.
- You aint seen nothing yet.
- I haven't seen enough.
I know that.
- You disappoint me though.
- How is that?
- A gentleman always
offers a lady a drink.
- What's a lady drink?
Pour yourself some.
- No.
Straight from the bottle for me.
Come closer.
- Bitch.
Drop the bottle now.
Liar.
Get into the safe room now.
- Copy that, heading
to the safe room now.
- Ow, ow.
- You're hurting me.
- I'm devastated by that.
- I just didn't trust you.
- Too late to be an apologist.
- I'll do whatever you want.
- Oh, I know you will.
- Okay the principles.
Okay our theory of coexistence
on both time periods.
The time distortion allows it.
- So wait a minute.
How do you know that
there's a distortion?
- Because it's one of the
basics of time and space.
In order to make
any time travel trip
you have to bend or rip that.
- And so you postulate
that this distortion
allows for an entity
to exist in both sides
of the time and both
sides of the bend.
- Yes.
- Yeah, like a mirror.
- But instead of
a reflection of
atomic light particles
it's a reflection of
atomic carbon particles.
- Yes.
- The person is
the reflection and like
the light particles
they exist on both sides.
- Yeah.
- Exactly.
- Brilliant.
- Yeah.
- F equals MA, mate.
Take everything we
have said as read.
But now we have another problem.
- The time that exists in
between the two periods
that's what we haven't
figured out yet.
- Let me have a try at it.
- Yeah, please.
- And I thought you
came to interview me
for a book.
- Yeah, we do.
- It's fine if you don't.
I mean we're all sort of
brothers in arms in this.
But let's have a look at this.
Alright, if you
take this equation
and you get rid of this.
This didn't come from
any equation of mine.
- Nope, we read all of
your materials every day.
Actually, it's just you.
- Don't mistake middle
age for gullible.
- We were inspired
professor by circumstance.
- Where did the
question come up?
Why would it be
necessary to answer some?
What's that?
- It's just a tattoo.
- Who do you work for?
- What do you mean?
- I've seen barcode tattoos
before and I've always thought
they were sort of an
odd personal choice.
But let me see it?
That a sign that
only lets you know
that was not a scar once.
Who do you work for?
- No one.
We're alone, professor.
- Where are you from?
- That's kinda hard to explain.
- Try explaining
it scientifically.
- How about we explain
it hypothetically.
- Yeah.
- There are two chaps
trapped in a past
they don't belong to.
They've made the
trip from a future
they don't want to go back to.
And they're trying
to change things.
And we need some help.
- What happened?
Hypothetically?
- Hypothetically speaking,
let's say they got disconnected
from the future.
- You can't get
disconnected from the future
because if you disconnect
the time space continuum
then they would
just cease to exist.
- And yet here we are.
- They are.
- Here they are.
- Yeah.
- Hypothetically.
- Well perhaps not then.
- Problem they face professor
is that they can't get home.
- How did they
get here or to this time
in the first place?
- Let's say they built
a machine of some sort.
- The one that bent the
temporal distortion.
- Yes.
- Why don't they just build
another machine and go back?
- Because you can't build a
machine to travel forward.
- Then they are stuck here.
Living out someone
else's future.
- They could send a
message to the future
and the machine
could reconstructed.
And then, they could
reconnect to the continuum.
And possibly that way
they might get home.
- That'll work.
- Yeah.
- Oh how about that?
- Thank you so much professor.
- Wait aren't you guys
coming back to my office?
- Oh, we have to go now.
- Look I've got like
a thousand questions
I've got to ask.
- Professor I promise we're
come and see you again
- and we'll talk.
- Yeah.
- Can I see your arm?
- It's the same as his.
- Please?
- Is this what we have
to look forward to?
- Not if we can help it.
- Good luck.
- You too.
- So what do you think?
- About what?
- About sending a message.
- I think it's worth a try.
- That creep built this cage.
It's got to have
a freaking flaw.
- What are you
doing, what's wrong?
- He was watching
us the entire time.
Listening to every word.
Just waiting.
- I know you're
watching us creep.
I dare you to come down
here and that with me.
- I messed up David pretty bad.
- And you did nothing?
- It's not fair.
- None of this is fair Jenny.
- Oh, I see so.
If I'm not screaming
at the walls
I'm not doing us any good?
- Oh yeah, whatever you're
doing isn't doing us any good.
- Well at least I'm
doing something.
I'm not just criticizing.
- Okay, okay.
Trying to seduce some guy is
that what we're doing now?
- What do you want from me, huh?
- Look I miss Thomas and
my brother just as much
as you, okay.
What do you think
they're doing to David?
- Besides Thomas, Nico.
David's the only one
who knows the machine.
What do you think
they're doing Lauren?
- You think he'll break?
- Everybody breaks.
Everybody breaks.
- Aright the safe contains
an acidic substance.
If anyone forces it
the vial will break
and all data will be lost.
Jenny
I love you.
You're the only one who has
the combination to this.
Got it.
- How was it?
- It's good.
- Okay.
Oh.
- Oh, hey Doc.
How's your father?
- Alive, he's alive.
A sunburst of energy.
We had the kind of conversations
we had back in the day.
- That's good to hear.
- We have the
blueprints for you now.
We're gonna give it to you
the next time we see you.
We need you to put it in a safe.
You know where and you know
how we want it rigged right?
- Yes.
- Now Doc, my wife has
the combination to this.
You know when it's
the right time.
- Incredible to think of that.
I'll do my best to make sure
that everything happens
the way it should.
- No don't try too hard.
Just live your life.
- But you are a
part of that right?
Aren't you?
- I suppose that's true.
- When you meet with the nurse
I've given her all the
information you requested
along with some cash.
- Thanks Doc.
- It's the least
that I could do.
I told you I could
never repay you.
- You don't need to.
You're a good man.
- You mentioned a list?
- Yeah, we need their addresses.
- From who?
- There's eight of
them that are pivotal
to this BIOCORP project
that we're dealing with.
They're a huge key to
the launch of the virus.
- And what will you do to them?
- What we have to.
- Hopefully they listen
and do the right thing.
- But if they don't Doc,
you know what's at stake.
- I have to go.
- Look we need it
soon though, Doc okay.
- I understand.
Give the list of
names to the nurse
along with the data.
- And I'll work on it quickly.
- Okay thanks Doc.
Talk to you soon.
- So this list huh?
It's a death list.
How do you want to handle that?
- Split it up.
- You know I think we
should stick together.
- No, cover more
ground that way.
- We'll save time.
- Ah, time.
That precious commodity
that we have so little
and so much of.
- We don't have much
time here though.
- Did you mean what you said?
About killing those
that don't listen?
- It's only our
last resort, okay.
- Yeah.
Just worried about
the Butterfly Effect.
- I am too.
Thomas this may
be our only chance
to ensure we have a future.
Nico, what if something
else happens, huh?
I don't know.
What if a meat virus happens?
They'll start killing
everybody in the meat factory.
- Thomas.
We both know that
doesn't happen.
- It might, Nico.
We're here, we're
changing things.
- But you heard the professor.
We can't change the past.
- This isn't our past.
This isn't some date
and time we read about
in a history book.
This doesn't belong to us.
It's different.
Our past is gone.
Our future's gone.
We're changing everything.
- The future's here.
My wife is here.
- I'm not blind to why we're
doing what we're doing, Nico.
I miss her too.
I'm just saying we
gotta be careful.
- We are being careful.
We have to be brave too.
- Yeah.
This place.
Feels different.
Cold.
Empty.
Doesn't feel like home.
Not without them.
- We can make it home.
Starting today.
I miss them too.
- Senator.
Thank you very much
for seeing me sir.
- Ah, you're
welcome, have a seat.
So.
How can I help you?
- Well actually, I
think it's more about
how I can help you.
I've heard that line before.
And it usually means
I help you first.
- Okay fair enough.
But Senator
what is the single greatest
threat people face?
Whether on foreign
or domestic soil?
- Terrorism.
- Of course.
Whether it's violent
or cyber or whatever.
What do all the
intelligence agencies
always like to complain
about lacking the most?
- Intelligence.
- Assets.
Because when you
really think about it
what we like to
call intelligence
is really just the
process of gathering
as much information as possible
from as many different
sources as possible.
- What are these?
- Oh those?
Those sir, that's
just the future.
- The future?
Huh?
- It's because I have
a vision of a world
that we'll all be
able to live in.
It has absolutely zero crime.
Zero.
Because every single
person is gonna be able
to be tracked via a computer
and microchip networking system
that we are going to build.
And that way, if somebody
does commit a crime
they will instantaneously
be able to be tracked,
apprehended, and prosecuted
in accordance with the law.
Never again will
someone get away with...
- Ray give me a moment please?
- Yes sir.
- I'm listening Mr. Tinker.
How does this work?
- So is gonna work?
I mean it's the only way we're
gonna get around separately.
I know but why would
you give me a car?
I don't exactly got money.
- Don't worry about
that, I got that covered.
Use this card once and
toss it, throw it away.
- I guess I'll wait out here.
- I'll be right back.
- Well?
- How are we gonna get
the people to swallow
this potentially bitter pill?
I mean, allowing them
all to be tagged.
I mean convincing our own people
is gonna be tough enough.
But you are telling me
that the entire world
is going to fall in line.
- You don't advertise
it by saying,
"Oh, you're gonna
be safe from crime".
You make the people want it.
- Go on.
- Well, guess we gotta
take care of business.
- Well let's not mess this up.
- Don't look at me
when you say that.
- We gotta do whatever it
takes to change the world.
- Yeah, good luck.
Hey Nicholai?
Let's give them a chance to
change their minds, okay.
- I'm the compassionate
one, remember.
- I know but I messed up
with that BIOCORP guy.
And I think if we
give them a chance
we could save everybody.
- I agree.
See you soon.
- These are medical files.
Ingenious, the chip is some
sort of medical device.
This indicates that
you have been sitting
on the cure for cancer.
- Remember that pill
we were talking about?
- Yeah.
- That's how we sweeten it up.
Not only that but
the chip is capable
of monitoring, storing,
and transmitting
life saving immediate
bodily functions.
- I mean, what are the
people going to think
when they find out that
they are being monitored
all the time?
- They'll know they're
being saved from cancer.
They're gonna sign up for it.
I mean, we're not gonna
hide the fact from 'em.
And at first it's gonna
feel a little overwhelming
but this is gonna
go down in history
as being the single
greatest act of security
in the history of mankind.
Period Barnon.
- What's in it for
me, specifically?
- Power.
Money.
Your place in history, sir.
You're going to be the
man that cures cancer.
I mean, you're going to be
able to write your own check.
Do you want to be President?
Do you want your
son to be President?
I mean, what do you want?
Because of you, no one is ever
gonna have to live in fear.
Because of you no one is
going to die of cancer.
Because of you no one
is ever gonna have
to fear for their safety again.
No one's ever gonna
be scared of crime
or vandalism or assault
or anything such as that.
Because of you everyone's
gonna feel safe.
Because of you never
again are parents
ever gonna loose a child
and be left wondering why.
That will never happen again.
Because of you, Senator.
- You're gonna have the
support of the Senate.
- Thank you Senator.
You just took a vital step
in making this world safe.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Pick up the pace.
- I'm trying.
- Try harder.
- Shh.
- He's coming.
- Good morning girls.
- How long do you plan
on keeping us here?
- Depends.
- On what?
- Your cooperation.
- You stupid enough to think
you could really control this?
- Shut your mouth woman.
Before I shut it for you.
- You'll ruin everything.
- Certain events
must be set right.
- You'll destroy us all.
- Time is like a pond.
- What?
- Imagine a stone,
it hits water.
It creates a ripple, it's chaos.
It changes everything forever.
- But it's only temporary.
The body of water will
become calm again.
The body of water
is still there.
- And so is the stone.
- It's changed forever.
- But it's one small stone.
- One small stone that
can kill a young boy
and make him slip and
crack his head open
or to kill the savior
of the Venetian.
- My children have
suffered too long.
What kind of man would
I be to let it continue?
- Your men are like sheep.
- You watch your step with me.
You don't understand anything.
- Oh, I understand completely.
It's like killing a
dictator as a young boy.
You don't know if you can
end up with someone worse.
- I've heard these
stories before.
- Yeah, well then why don't
you start listening to them.
- Enough.
- Don't touch her.
- Is that any way to
speak to your father?
Open the cell.
- What are you gonna do?
- Take her to my room.
- No, no, no, please.
Get out of here.
- Lauren.
What is wrong with you?
Lauren.
♪ See a road
♪ Where I go
♪ Where you go
♪ You
♪ See a man
♪ No one knows
♪ And I've got
hope in my hands ♪
♪ Please keep me warm
♪ With your love
♪ I'm gonna fly to the moon
♪ Oh I'm alone with your love
♪ I see a shape
♪ No mistake
♪ You see a lie
♪ No more time
♪ Mo more time
♪ To deny
♪ I've got my mind on you
♪ My mind on you
♪ No more time
♪ To deny
♪ I've got my mind on you
♪ My mind on you
♪ I've got hope
♪ In my hands
♪ Please keep me warm
♪ With your love
♪ I'm gonna fly to the moon
♪ Oh I'm alone
♪ With your love
♪