Previously on Dystopia.
- The safe box has
an acidic substance.
So if it's forced open the vial
will break and all
data will be lost.
- There's gotta be a
way to crack this open.
- So where's this place?
- There's a community of people
that are living outside
of BIOCORP world.
- Okay, we'll get
our guy out there.
- Activate.
- Dead soldiers are free,
prep for the next one.
- We're gonna get that combo.
- Abandon your ID
Chip program research.
- My director of special programs,
he oversees everything.
He will know exactly
what is going on.
- I will ask him...
- What's his name?
- Brandon...
- Brandon what?
- Davidson.
- You mentioned a list?
- We need their addresses.
There's eight of
them that are pivotal
to this BIOCORP project
that we're dealing with.
They're a huge key to
the loss of the virus.
- And what will you do to them?
- Let's give 'em a
chance to change their minds.
- Hey, I'm the
compassionate one, remember?
- Open the cell, take her.
- Lauren, Lauren!
- Did I ever
tell you about my dad?
- No.
- I didn't?
- He used to make this
pig snorting noises
to cheer me up if he
thought I was depressed.
Serious, that was
his thing he did.
- Make pig noises?
- Mm-hmm, yeah, all the time.
- Did it work?
- No, not once ever, but
he did it like it did.
You know, it was like his thing.
Oh, you're upset,
let me do this.
It was terrible.
Excuse me, can we
get another one?
- Yeah.
- Another one?
- Another two.
- Another two, okay.
- What'd it sound like?
- Like it was a proper pig
snorting, like a.
- Like a real?
- Like that would make
somebody be happy again.
I used to hate it.
He did it in front
of all my friends.
I'm sure it lost me
like four girlfriends.
- Maybe more than that.
- And I was already the
Brit kid in America.
I didn't need another
reason to be bullied.
- What happened to him?
- He died in the riots.
It was okay, you know,
because he was a hero to me.
He died saving my mum.
You know, died protecting
the woman he loved.
Worse ways to go than that.
But everyday since
that, I was thinking
I hated that pig snorting noise
and I would give anything
to hear it one more time.
- Were you there when he died?
- No.
- Why don't you try to find him?
We're here.
- What would I say?
We're time-travelers
from the future
trying to save the world.
- Well, I wouldn't start the
conversation that way, but...
- Yeah, I know.
- Listen we got time,
you should at least try.
- I did, I found him.
- Where?
- He's sitting at
the end of the bar.
- What are you waiting for?
- What would I say to him, Nico?
Would I tell him
he doesn't make it?
Would I tell him my
mum doesn't make it?
Would I tell him none
of us are gonna make it?
I'm not gonna do that to him.
I'm not gonna upset him.
Although I did think
of a way to make
his day today just
a little happier.
- What's that?
- I could buy him a beer.
- Excuse me, can I get
one more shot please
and a beer for the gentleman
at the end of the bar.
- Today Nobel Peace Prize-winning
BIOCORP made history
by administering the
cure for cancer available
to the entire world's
population in exchange
for their compulsory enrollment
in the ID chip program
which allows for increased
population security.
BIOCORP CEO stated, "We have
all suffered loss in our lives,
"when our loved ones are stolen
from us before their time.
"Today we fight for
the people we love.
"We can't hold on just
a little bit longer."
And that's all for tonight.
- And, we're clear.
- Hey, baby.
- What's going on?
We need to figure this out.
- We're losing them!
- Oh my God, help me!
Let me out!
Oh, my God!
- We are wasting time.
- We are getting close.
- Close, that's
your idea of close?
30 attempts, 30 dead volunteers,
that's what you call close?
- The variables are too vast.
We need more data.
- Isn't that what we are
paying these scientists for?
- Whoever was here locked
us out of the protocols
as a fail-safe against
replicating the workflow.
They're a disappointment.
- Well then replace
them, right now!
Replace them, get
these out of here, out.
- Alright, let's go.
- I want your best scientists.
- I don't know if anyone else
would be any more successful.
- What are you saying?
- Protocols, they're encoded.
- Well then find someone
to break the codes!
- Those women from the
apartment, they would know how.
They maybe even set the code.
- Great, do we know
where they are?
- Our scanners show
that they're with
The Unity of Lost
Children terrorist cell.
- Oh, that degenerate,
so he adopted
two more daughters
into his household.
- Disgusting group.
- Get the women and
bring them here.
- And The Lost Children?
- Leave them in the ground,
just get the girls here!
Incompetence.
- Yes?
- Brandon Davidson?
- Yes.
- You've bungled
this whole situation
from the very beginning!
Your inability to deal with
your people and your
responsibilities.
- Please forgive
me, Mr. President.
- The hell with forgiveness!
If you can't do your job then
I'll get somebody who can.
You understand?
- Yes sir, I do.
- What about the technology,
can it be replicated?
- Our people are
working on it right now.
- If it's replicated
we're gonna need a lot
of those little chambers and
we're gonna need 'em fast.
- Of course sir, but I'll need
more men and more resources.
- And you'll have 'em.
In the meantime, you
send your best man
to hunt down those
bastards, you get it?
- Sir, we're still unsuccessful
with proper stasis thus far.
- Then figure it out!
We're running out of time.
- Yes, Mr. President.
- I want somebody to
keep an eye on him.
- He's our top man, sir.
- I hope I'm our top man.
Anybody else, I don't trust.
- Shh, shh, don't, don't move!
Hey, stop, stop, stop,
stop it, don't move.
- Okay
- Don't move, don't move.
- Please don't hurt me!
- Hey, shh!
Keep your voice,
keep your voice down.
- Okay, okay.
- Keep your voice down.
- Please, I have
credit cards, I have...
- Hey stop, I'm not
here to rob you.
- Okay, okay, please.
- I'm not here to rob you.
- Please don't.
I'm not here to rob you.
- I'm a married
woman, please don't.
- Shh, I'm not here
for that, either.
- What do you want?
What do you want?
- I wanna kill you, Kyla.
- How do you, how
do you know my name?
How do you know my name?
- I know a great deal about
you, about the future.
- What?
What?
My future?
What are you talking about?
- You don't believe me,
you wouldn't believe.
- What's your name?
- Thomas is my name.
- Thomas, okay Thomas,
why are you doing this?
- Because I'm saving the world.
I'm saving the future.
- Okay.
- Hey!
- Get out.
- Stop it, stop it.
Do you think I'm stupid?
- No, no, no, I don't.
- Put your hands on the wheel,
put your hands on the wheel.
- Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, Thomas.
Just tell me about
the future, Thomas.
- Don't do that, don't
try and play with me.
Don't try and handle me.
- Don't try and talk me down.
- No, I...
- Okay, I'm not
to be toyed with.
- I won't and I'm not, I'm not.
- You don't believe me?
You don't believe what
I'm gonna say to you.
That you and our future
share something in common.
Infertility.
- What?
What?
- That's right,
I know about you.
I know all about you.
I know that you've been trying
to have a baby for a year.
- How?
- Seeing doctor after
doctor after doctor
and nothing helped.
I know that you're
seeing a specialist
next month and that
won't help either.
- You don't know
that, you bastard!
- You don't know that!
- Yes, I do.
Yes, I do.
- No, you don't know.
- All that lies ahead for you,
Kyla, is a crushing defeat.
It'll never happen.
- Why are you doing this?
- See, that pain
and that anguish
that you feel right now, that
hopelessness, that despair?
You multiply that by
six billion people
and you have what happens
in our world because of you.
- I'm sorry, but I don't know
what you're talking about.
- I'm sorry too, Kyla!
- Oh, God!
- I really am, but
I gotta do this.
- Stop it.
- Please don't!
- Stop!
- Please don't, please don't!
- Please don't kill me!
- Give me one good reason.
- Please, please.
- My husband, I'm all
he has left, please!
Please, please!
- Why should I care about
you or your husband?
- Don't you have someone
to live for, please?
- Better than that, I've got
someone worth killing for.
- No, something good,
something to fight for.
Something to get back to,
where the pain isn't so much.
- Yeah.
- Please, you're not a monster.
- Shut up.
- Please, please.
Shut up.
- Oh, my!
Oh, my God!
- For over half a century
BIOCORP has been working to
protect you and your children.
At the cutting-edge of
pharmaceutical research,
nano-technology, and
disease prevention.
Our goal is to keep you safe.
BIOCORP, protecting our future.
For over half a century...
- Tell the generals to start
drawing up contingency plans
for putting an end
to the rebels, okay?
- Eliminating them?
- Yeah, it's time to
put an end to this.
- Yes, Mr. President.
- Ming, this is Luke, come in.
Ming, this is Luke, come in.
Ming, this is Luke,
you receiving?
- Ming, receiving.
- Anything?
- I've reached the town.
- What do you see?
- I don't see much,
it looks pretty quiet.
- They can't be that
difficult to find, surely.
There's meant to be a
whole community there.
- It doesn't look like
anyone's been here for years.
I'm gonna go check some
more of the houses.
- Alright, well
remember, they're hiding.
So look everywhere!
- Copy.
- I know what you're thinking.
You think we're evil,
sending a guy out there,
over the wall, alone, in danger.
But what's at stake here
is bigger than anyone!
- Spare me the
justification speech.
- I do wonder if there's
anything actually out there
in the dust or
anything to hope for.
Anything.
But right now I suspect
that there is nothing
and that this whore is
lying to me to buy time.
And that's what this
is all about, time.
- Sir, there's nothing here.
What do you want me to do?
- Brought you a peace offering.
Have a drink.
- No.
- I'm just trying to make
this easier on you, you know.
Did anyone ever tell you
how beautiful you are?
I hate this part,
but I'm afraid it must be done.
Authority must be
respected at all times.
Wouldn't you agree, Lauren?
- I know the combination.
- What?
- Jenny knows it, too.
She just didn't wanna tell you.
- Then give it up.
- I'll give it to
you if you let us go.
- Deal.
- It's when Jenny's baby died.
- Which is?
- Zero seven, zero
five, three six.
- That's my girl, you
did the right thing.
Three six.
Did you just play me?
- You weren't gonna let
us go were you, Travis?
I'd rather die than let anything
happen to Thomas or Nico.
- There are worse
things than death.
- Let go of me!
- Stay still!
- Get off!
No!
- You leave her alone,
you leave her alone!
- What are you gonna do, huh?
What, you gonna ride in there
on a white horse and save her?
- Stop it, you're a monster!
- How can you let
him do this to her?
- He is our leader,
he trained us.
We would do anything for him!
If he wants to have some
fun who I am to stop him?
- She's not one of you.
- Things change.
- Okay, okay, go on.
- Do it, you bastard.
- No.
- You coward.
- I won't yet, I know you
know the code to that safe.
- Yeah, I do actually.
And I was about
five seconds away
from opening the thing
when you idiots came in.
Should have been a
little more patient, huh?
Idiot!
Now you're never
gonna get it open.
- Level
cleared, moving upstairs.
- Take them outta here.
How do you feel now, child?
- Just do it.
Do it!
- Keep your eyes
on the second target.
Careful, we need this one alive.
- Two on him, two on him.
- Let's go, get up!
- Room secure.
- Is this their
patriarch of the family?
- Yes, sir.
- Thank you.
- Don't thank me yet.
Watch her.
You know, I might even get a
promotion after your execution.
- You will never silence
The Lost Children.
- You're nothing
but a fear-monger.
All your attempts to spread
chaos and terror have failed.
- I don't know about that.
She seemed terrified of me.
- Hold it.
My dear, how would you like
to experience true power?
- What?
- This is true power.
It gives the ultimate
advantage to whoever wields it.
Brave men crumble
in the face of it.
- What do you mean?
- Allow me to demonstrate.
- You see how even
Travis gets nervous
at the thought of death?
I don't think he's quite
ready to die for his cause.
Nope, not yet.
- What are you doing?
- I'm giving you
control, kill him.
Kill the bastard that raped you.
- I can't.
- Sure you can, his
death is warranted.
Think of all the
crimes he's committed,
all the atrocities his
so-called Children relish in.
- She doesn't have the guts.
- That's it.
- She's not gonna do it.
She's not gonna sully
her hands on me.
- See how he mocks you?
Are you gonna give
him the satisfaction?
Are you gonna let him win?
- Do it!
- There, you even
have his permission.
Either you kill him quickly
or my men will do it slowly.
- I can't.
- I knew you couldn't do it.
You're nothing but a stupid...
You're welcome.
This will all be over soon.
- The human race?
- Always so dramatic.
You spend so much
time fighting us
you fail to see the
reality of the situation,
that the Speaker's
intentions are good.
- Good?
How do you figure that exactly?
- He rescued you from the
terrorist cell, didn't he?
- Out of the frying
pan into the fire.
- It's an appropriate metaphor.
- Why do you follow him blindly?
- I owe him my life.
- Does that make
you the only one?
- You don't understand,
what he did for me
I would proudly serve
him 'til the day I die.
- Are we gonna be okay?
- We will, I promise.
- I wouldn't make any
promises you can't keep.
- Sir, we're
clearing the terrorist base.
Just awaiting your
permission to set the bomb.
Leave no survivors.
- Roger that.
- Hey, how's the mission going?
- A lot tougher than I expected.
- Tough for anybody.
- I really tried
to be reasonable with him.
- What happened?
- I killed Brandon Davidson
in front of his kids today.
- We're almost there, mate.
- Yeah, almost, but not quite.
I just wonder...
- What about?
- Sometimes I just
wonder that...
- What?
I wonder if the people
that we're approaching,
if they know what
they're doing is bad
if it's gonna end up
bad in the future.
- No mate, they don't know.
What makes you say that?
- Because the guy that
I got the chip from today,
he made a duplicate,
he kept in a safe.
He protected it like he knew
what it was capable of doing.
- Damn.
Where's the chip now?
- I got it.
- Destroy it.
- It's done.
Are we doing the
right thing, Thomas?
- We're saving the world, Nico.
- Yeah, I guess in a way we are.
I just don't know how much
longer I can keep this up.
- You can do this, mate.
- You're right, I can, I can.
- There's the Nico
we all know and love.
Are you getting any sleep?
- Barely man, if I
do it's nightmares.
- Yeah, yeah, I've been
having a few of those.
- About what?
- My nightmare, Nico,
it's us failing,
not being able to get home.
- All that work and we're
just gonna sit here?
Who the hell do you...
- Alright, my apologies, I
had to finish the chapter.
It's my favorite book.
Well done, Commander.
- Thank you, sir.
- So, isn't this
a nice surprise?
I trust your journey
was comfortable?
- What do you want?
- And I take it you're not
one for pleasantries, then.
Alright, then I'll
get right to it.
BIOCORP has grown
in profits and power
far more than even I
ever could have imagined.
But if I could go back and
do it over again, of course
there are improvements
that I would make.
- It's all about the profits.
- Commander, Commander, please.
We know my distaste for
unnecessary violence.
I mean, what would
the children think?
So, today is your lucky day.
You're just in time
to see another one
of our attempts at
using those machines.
The past results
have been disastrous.
Normally, we would use
one of our soldiers,
but to celebrate
your arrival today,
we're going to use
one of your friends
from The Unity of Lost Children.
- What?
No!
Get off of me!
Stop!
- Finally got your attention.
Prep him, now!
- So how did it go with
BIOCORP's head of security?
Did you talk to him?
- I tried, but he...
He didn't listen.
Don't forget why we're
doing what we're doing.
- Yeah, for the children.
- How many more are there?
- I'm half-way.
- Me, too.
- I guess you'd better
get back to work.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Hi, how are you?
- Honey, what did I tell you
about talking to strangers?
I'm so sorry.
- No, it's not a problem.
- What's your name?
- You don't ask strangers that!
- No, I told you, it's
not a problem, really.
My name is Nicholai.
What's your name?
- Jenny.
- That's a beautiful name.
- Thank you.
- Say goodbye to the nice man.
- Bye.
- You have to be careful
to who you talk to Jenny.
- I'll see you again.
- So, as I understand it,
the computer systems
hold the data
for the proper
teleportation protocols
but, they seem to be encoded.
Well...
I need those protocols.
I'll ask you again.
Nothing?
No one?
Well, then.
- No, Lauren!
- I'll ask you again.
- Wait.
- I want the protocols.
I want them now.
- Wait, wait.
- Don't say anything.
- I have no problem
killing either one of you.
Tell me.
Your friend, soldier,
bring him out here.
Bring him out, come
on, to the right!
I want the protocols, now!
Do you think you're
safe with someone?
We will get this working
eventually with or without you
and when we do I will
see that it will be used
to hunt down and kill every
member of your families.
You will all be wiped clean
from the history of this planet!
Now give me the protocols!
- Go ahead, do it!
- No, no!
- No, no, no let him.
Let him show us just how
powerful a man he is.
- Alright.
Do you really wanna
see another woman die?
- Please, please, I'll
show you how it works.
- Good boy.
- No, what they're
doing is more important.
- I can't live with this.
- What, what?
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- You made a very
astute decision.
But do you think I
really trust you?
- What?
- Soldier, get him out of here.
It's your lucky day, young man.
We're going to send her.
- No, no, I'll send her.
- Really?
- Everyone you've sent is dead!
You don't know what
you're doing, but I do.
To show you how it works, to
show you we can be trusted.
I'll send her and then
afterwards we go free.
- Fine.
- What are you doing?
- I'm saving our lives.
- No, I'm not his guinea pig!
- I don't have time for
these domestic squabbles!
If you don't get going
I will put a bullet
in each of your heads in 10
seconds and I swear to it.
- Let me test the
machine to make sure
your men haven't damaged it.
- Of course, my men
have damaged it.
If I was certain that it was
working you'd be dead by now!
Now you're wasting
my time, go, go!
Commander.
- No, David, David, no!
- Stand down from that post.
- Let go of me!
David!
Let go of me!
- Oh, shut up!
- David!
- System unlocked,
welcome back, David.
Time displacement
protocols loaded.
- Well?
- I can't tell until I've
run a full diagnostics.
- And how long will that take?
- A day, maybe two.
- Are you kidding me?
That's totally unacceptable!
- Listen to me, this isn't just
an issue of killing
person after person.
The only way to
know if the machine
is working properly or not,
which is what you want,
is for me to test
the mechanism first.
- No.
- Then I'll send Jenny
through when I'm sure.
- He does have a point, sir.
- Do you really think I hate you
so much I'd kill
the woman I love?
I'd do anything for her,
anything to save her.
- That's reasonable.
I'd say it's even admirable.
Commander, how do we know that
the machine won't
work right now?
Have her strapped
in the machine.
- Wait, what?
- Yes, sir.
- No, let go of me!
- We'll send her.
- Let go of me!
- And if she dies
I'll do whatever you ask.
- Get off of me!
- You can take all the time
you want with your diagnostics.
You, scientists!
Listen, watch.
I want to get rid of these
people as soon as possible.
- Wait, wait, wait, just let me!
- Really, I thought it
would take a day or two?
One or two days.
- What's that?
- It's an anesthetic.
- Go confirm what's
in that syringe.
- It's the only way it works.
They have to be
asleep on either end
before they go
through or they die.
- You idiots couldn't
figure that out on your own?
- System ready, David.
- Track the microchip.
- I hope we have
success with this one.
- We might.
What are you saying to her?
- I'm just trying
to help her relax.
She has to be in a coma-like
state before she goes through.
You only have an
hour to put yourself
to sleep before
you come back in.
- Okay.
- Don't waste time exploring.
Find Nico and come home.
- David.
I didn't know.
- See you soon.