Previously on Dystopia.
- You mentioned a list?
- We need their addresses.
There's eight of
them that are pivotal
to the Biocorp project
that we're dealing with
and they're a huge key to
the launch of the virus.
We are getting close.
- 30 attempts, 30
dead volunteers,
that's what you call close.
- Yeah, but are you
sure that's the right guy?
- It's definitely the right guy.
- All right, change the future,
but you can not change the past.
- You're in our future.
She has something in common.
Infertility.
And that pain and that anguish
that you feel right now,
multiply that by
6,000,000,000 people
and you have what happens in
our world, because of you.
- Have her strapped
into the machine.
- Do you really
think I hate you so much
I'd kill the woman I love?
I'd do anything for her.
- And now for
tonight's top story.
Today Nobel Peace Prize
winning Biocorp made history
by administering
the cure for cancer,
available to the entire
world's population
in exchange for their
compulsory enrollment
in the I.D. Chip
Program, which allows for
increased population security.
Bio Corp CEO stated, we are
at the precipice of change,
which always feels unnerving,
but what changes we make today
will echo in time and our
children will thank us
for embracing the new world.
That's all for tonight.
- And we're all clear.
- Hi babe.
- Was it a good news day?
- I don't know baby, we're
gonna have to wait and see.
- When will we know?
- I guess we'll find out
by the end of the day.
Now I heard that my baby wants
some chocolate ice cream.
- Yeah.
- Mrs. Adams.
- Yes.
- I'm David Johnson
from Biocorp.
It's time for your
I.D. chip enrollment.
- That was fast.
- We believe that
the media should be
the first to jump on
board, set a great example.
- Of course.
Come on, baby.
- Track the microchip.
Find Nico.
- What are you saying to her?
- I'm just trying
to help her relax.
She has to be in a coma like
state before she goes through.
Now remember, you
only have an hour
to put yourself to sleep
before we pull you back in.
Don't waste time exploring.
Find Nico and come home.
- Watch everything
he does, gentlemen.
Jenny connected.
Displacement initiated.
- Did it work?
- Her brain activity
is comparable
with somebody who's awake.
- What does that mean?
- It means it worked.
She's in the past.
- What year?
- 2017.
- Excellent, bring her back.
- But we have to
wait the full hour.
- Pull her back right now.
- If you pull her
back now, she'll die.
- I find that of little concern.
Bring her back now.
- Well then you won't
know if the machine
is working properly or not.
You wanna know if it works?
We gotta do it right.
- Don't toy with me, son.
- She has 55 minutes.
- What are you typing?
- I'm taking notes on
her brain activity,
her heart rate, her temperature
and her blood pressure
just to make sure there's
no significant changes.
- I trust all you gentlemen
are paying attention
here please?
- We're getting
it all down, sir.
- So if this all works, I
decided not to execute you.
And instead have you
work for Biocorp,
but I will agree to
release her, if it works.
Well you can think about
it, but it's easy really,
live and work for
Biocorp, or die.
- The deal we had...
- The deal's changed, keep up.
- What are you
planning to do with it?
You could destroy everything
by meddling with the past.
- I didn't create it.
Those were your
meddlesome friends.
You think they
had lofty motives.
I'm sure they're
creating havoc already.
- No, they stumbled
on it by accident.
- Oh yes, this is
clearly all an accident.
- No, it's true.
They didn't want any
of this to happen.
- Well, be that as it may,
I will use it to go back and
change things for the better.
- Tampering with the past could
threaten our very existence.
Look, I will do everything
you want, but she has to live.
- Why would you risk
your life for her?
- Cause that's just what
friends do for one another.
- Friends?
The word friend has
no true meaning here.
We are creatures
of want and need.
Those you call friends
merely satisfy you.
- I think you're confused.
Just put the gun
down and we can talk.
- Tell me about Biocorps.
- I told you, I don't
know anything about that.
- You're lying.
This is all your fault.
You're probably one of her.
You started the whole
thing, didn't you?
You tried it on your
child, didn't you?
- No, you're crazy.
- You think you're
better than us?
I am crazy, but you're
a genocidal stain.
You're a genocidal stain!
Listen to me, listen to me.
If you even come close to
making Bio Corp succeed
or support them, I
swear I will kill you.
Do you understand?
Say you understand!
- I understand.
I understand.
- All right, enough time.
Do it now.
- No, it's not time.
- Do it now.
- Look at her brain activity.
- I don't care.
Do what I say.
- Her brain wave patterns
say she's not asleep yet.
If you wake her up
now, it'll kill her.
- I think you two
are up to something.
- You told me to run
the machine properly.
You knew that she
has to be in stasis.
- And now I'm telling
you to bring her back.
- What is the point of
knowing how it works
if you won't let me
show you how it works?
That's insane!
- Do it now.
- I will not kill her.
- You're not looking to kill.
You're buying time.
Step aside, you're finished.
- What do you want
me to do with him?
- Kill him.
I won't have people
barking orders at me
like I'm one of their pets.
- How will you figure the exact
way to bring someone back?
- Try on her.
- Jenny?
Oh my gosh.
Oh, I can't believe it's you.
- It's done.
- Why then?
To happen to you?
- Jenny, my God.
Is Lauren with you?
- No, she...
- What happened, Jenny?
- I shot her.
- You shot... I shot her.
Who do you think
Biocorp, the speaker...
- What the hell happened to her?
- I can't explain now.
Biocorp is at the apartment
and they're going to
pull me back in six minutes.
- Sir, I think we should let him
finish showing the scientist.
He may be the only one left
who really knows the machine.
- He and that girl are
plotting against us
right now in the past.
- They had no time to plan that.
- You and I commander,
we're alive in 2017.
She could be hovering
over our young bodies,
planning to kill
us in our sleep.
- I hope she is.
- You see?
- You're all the same,
power hungry men without
a brain among you.
- And you're all the same,
so fierce in your convictions
as though they might save you.
- All due respect, sir,
I think we should let the
brain activity go to stasis,
like he says.
- Very well.
- Nico, look, I love
you and I miss you,
but you have to let me go.
- No, I'm not gonna lose you.
- I don't want to go either,
but you have to knock me out.
- No, I don't know what
you're talking about.
- They're gonna wake
me in five minutes.
- No, no, David's not gonna
do that unless it's safe.
- David has a gun to his...
- No, I'm not going
to lose you again.
- We have no other choice.
Please, you have to let me go.
Just put me under.
- Prepare the
adrenaline syringe.
Let's get this process going.
- You can't kill her.
- I told you, you're finished.
- Wait, if I, if you, let
her live, I will help you.
I will tell you everything
about the machine.
I will work for Biocorp
like you wanted.
With my help, you
can use this device
to take over the world.
There are secrets
about this machine
that I will tell you
only if you let her live.
- Really?
All right.
Except, you will tell
us these secrets now
or I guarantee you,
I will let her die.
- Why can't I just
stay here with you?
- No, no, no, no, you can't.
- Why not?
- You can't because,
because if you're asleep
there, you might die.
- I don't care.
I want to be with you.
I want to be with
the man that I love.
- I love you.
- I'm so sorry about Lauren.
- It's not your fault.
It's not your fault.
It's okay.
- David, he risked
his life for her.
- It's not your fault, baby.
- They just,
they killed her in cold blood.
- It's okay, just stay with me.
Stay with me, okay?
Just be with me.
- I am.
I am.
- Please, just let
her fall asleep.
You know this will kill her.
- What are these secrets?
- Wake her up properly first.
- We know the machine works.
We have enough
information to carry on
without you or without her.
What are the secrets?
- You do this, I'll never tell.
- You've got nothing.
The adrenaline.
- Wait.
- Tell me the secrets.
- I will when you,
wait, wait, wait, without
me, you will fail.
Back, back, back, back!
Get back, go farther!
- Shots fired, move, move, move!
- No, no, no!
- She'll live.
In a better future.
- No, no!
How could you let this happen?
- You all right?
- My head.
- I remember this
headache, it's okay.
- What?
Are, are they trying to wake me?
- They disconnected you, honey.
- How?
- They must have had no choice.
You're here now.
You shouldn't go back.
- I don't care, I don't care.
I just want to be with you.
- I know, I know.
It's okay.
We need to find Thomas, babe.
- She loved him.
You know that, don't you?
She loved you.
- Move it now,
take your corners.
- Oh, thank heavens
Like usual, you're just in time.
Get me a new team and
get rid of these bodies.
- Yes sir.
What now?
- What now?
I don't know, but thanks to you,
we do know how to go one way.
- Hello.
- Hello, is
this Mrs. Kyla Torres?
- Yes, speaking.
- Mrs. Torres, this
is Dr. Raymond Prentice,
at the New Jersey
fertility center.
- Yes, hello doctor,
how are you doing?
- Very well,
thank you for asking.
I'm calling in regards
to the recent tests
that you've undergone
here at the hospital.
- Yes, yes, doctor.
How'd they come out?
- Well Mrs. Torres,
I'm sorry to have
to tell you this,
there's really no easy
way of saying it but,
all of the tests have come back
and they're fairly conclusive.
In fact, they are
100% conclusive.
I'm afraid you are
completely infertile.
Beyond adoption or surrogacy,
I'm afraid you will
never have children.
Mrs Torres, I am...
Mrs. Torres?
Mrs. Torres, are you there?
Mrs. Torres.
- You are our future.
She has something in common.
Infertility.
- Oh my God.
He was right.
- Hey Thomas.
Thomas.
Are you crazy?
Put the gun down.
- We're committed
here, Nico, right?
We came here with a job to do
and now we have to finish it.
- Right, but put the gun down.
What did you lose your mind?
- Where's Jenny?
- She's uh,
she's in the motel.
- How is she still here?
- David, he's uh,
he did what he had to do.
She's here with us now.
- Lucky me.
Always the third wheel.
- It's gonna be okay, bud.
- I feel so alone, Nico,
in a way I thought
I'd never feel.
- We're in this together.
- I know.
- We're gonna find a way home.
- What are we going home to?
- The future.
The future buddy.
We've got the future.
- The future.
The future?
You have your future!
You have Jenny!
You have everything!
Lauren is gone!
A future without Lauren?
For me?
There is nothing left to see.
- I understand, but...
- No, no.
No you don't.
I get that you loved her.
I get that she's your sister.
I really do, I really do,
but you did not love her.
- Look, that is not my fault.
That is not my fault!
- Yes it is because you
allowed this to happen!
We left them and
we shouldn't have.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to, I'm sorry.
- Okay, it's all right.
- No, I'm not blaming you.
I know exactly, exactly
where the blame lies.
- We need to get our
heads straight, okay?
We're in danger.
- We're in danger?
- No, Jenny told me everything.
They got the machine.
They're sending people back.
They're gonna be quick and
they're gonna be brutal.
- It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter,
Nico, you hear?
Biocorp aren't the bully.
Here, we're the killers.
Biocorp, they're just babies.
- We're not killers.
We're not killers.
- Yes we are Nico.
We've killed.
How many people have we killed?
So many I don't even remember.
And we need to kill a few more.
You know what we need to do?
We need to kill just a few more.
We have to kill every
employee, every colleague,
every investor, every
friend, every mother,
every child of anything
to do with Biocorp.
We have to leave
no place standing.
- We didn't move here to
kill children, Thomas.
- If we leave Biocorp
standing, Nico,
that's exactly what we do.
- The global biological
clock is ticking against us.
At this time,
- Almost as if I
wrote it myself.
- I can't believe
everyone thinks
that's the real John Williams.
- Well, I'm not interested
in being famous.
I just wanna fix
this big mess here.
- Kyla.
- Oh, you again.
- Me again.
- I just want you to know,
I haven't done anything.
I haven't done anything wrong.
- Kyla,
I'm not here about that today.
- Okay, well, I took your
warning very seriously
and its been all
I can think about
and I even went to...
- Kyla, Kyla.
- What?
- I'm here to ask for a favor.
- I need you to
help me with access
to the Biocorp internal network.
- No, I, I, I can't...
Oh my God, holy...
- Shut up.
- Shut up, Kyla.
- Calm down.
- Stop talking!
I need the names and addresses
of every Biocorp employee.
- What, why do you need that?
- Stop talking and
start listening!
- Okay...
- Because the more you
talk, the angrier I get,
and the angrier I get,
the more I remember
you killed a whole
load of my friends
and then I just want to
blow your brains out.
- Okay, okay, okay.
We can access it
from my house, okay?
We can do that.
We can do that at
my house, okay?
Okay?
- Is this your car?
- Yes, yes, it's right here.
- Yeah.
- Then let's go.
- Okay.
- After you.
- You know what, you
really don't need that.
- Actually I do because I don't
trust anybody or anything.
- I told you that
you can trust me.
- After seeing what you
become in the future?
Why, I'll pass.
- So what, no faith that humans
can change for the better?
- Not really.
- What happened to you?
What made you so
goddamn cynical?
- Oh nothing big,
just all my friends
and all my family died.
Everybody I've ever
known is gonna die
and the woman I
love, I left to die.
I saw society tear
itself apart for an idea
that was supposed to save us,
all from your company.
- But that's not my fault.
- Actually, it is.
But you can change that.
Put all the information on this.
- Whatever you want.
Okay.
This is everything.
Done.
- Well done, Kyla.
What you're doing
is saving lives,
starting with your own.
Don't forget what I said.
Don't do anything stupid.
- I promise.
- We'll see.
- God, give me the serenity
to accept the things
I cannot change and the courage
to change the things I can
and the wisdom to
know the difference.
Oh my...
Commander.
- Sir.
- Report.
- We completed
repairs on the machine
and after reviewing
David's notes,
I think we're ready to successfully
send back a volunteer.
- Well done.
Hm.
You may proceed.
I'll inform the president.
- Yes, sir.
- Hey, you okay?
- Yeah, I'll be okay.
- She died trying
to save your life.
She never gave up,
not until the end.
So stubborn.
She kind of reminds
me of someone.
- I know he loved her.
Our father loved her
so much more than me.
I was pretty much
invisible to him.
I think that's why I
hated her growing up.
Well that and she
used to steal my toys.
- Well you got over
that eventually, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I did.
You know, for the
longest time, she was,
she was my only friend.
- And you
meant the world to her.
- God, it's my fault.
- No, it's not.
- I shouldn't have left, honey.
- You had to.
- No, I had a choice.
- Here she comes.
- No, no, just,
look, I knew they were
going to raid the apartment.
I felt it in my gut
and you know what?
I still took the chance on it.
I left you guys alone and
her and, I don't,
we went on a stupid mission
to save the world and
just made everything worse.
- No, you did what
you had to do.
- A lot of people
have had to die.
A lot.
- Babe, you are a good man.
You've always been a good man.
- How do you know?
- Because I married you and
I see it day in and day out.
And if what I say isn't
enough to convince you,
just know that the doctor
told me that you are too.
- He made it?
- Yeah, he was in our time.
He helped us.
- I didn't think he'd
remember after all this time.
- How could he forget?
You saved his father's life.
- That was Thomas.
- No, it was both of you.
He hadn't seen you in 20 years
and he still gave his
last moments to you.
Doesn't that speak volumes?
- Yeah, but you know, just,
it's just been hard.
A lot of people have had to
die so we can save lives.
- I know.
It's been hard for all of us.
- And Thomas, he's...
- Thomas,
he doesn't have it anymore.
He never really did.
- I don't know
what he's gonna do.
- It's Thomas we're
talking about.
- Hello.
Hi.
What is it that you have there?
- It's my ladybug.
- Oh, it's a big one.
- It's the biggest
I've ever seen.
- It's pretty.
- I'm gonna take
it home as a pet.
- Oh, that's nice of you.
- My brother's gonna hate it.
He doesn't like
creepy crawly things.
- Your brother.
I bet he's nice too.
- Not when he's sleepy.
Do you want to hold it?
- Who me?
- Yes you, silly.
- Okay.
Wow, she's pretty like you.
- Can I have it back now?
Yeah, sure.
There you go.
- I have to go feed her.
- You know, lettuce
is good for ladybugs.
- How do you know?
- How do I know?
I mean, I used to have
a ladybug as a pet.
- Really?
- Yeah.
My sister used to
bring 'em home to me
when I was a little boy.
- That's what I do.
- Sweetie, time to go.
- I have to go now.
Bye.
- Okay, bye bye.
- What's for dinner?
- Oh my God, okay.
So are you trying to
give me a heart attack?
- Perhaps.
- What do you want now?
What?
- I see why you're
childless, Kyla.
- Why, because I can't cook?
- No, because you
don't deserve one.
- What,
wait,
wait, did something happen?
- Oh yes.
Things have changed, Kyla.
- I gave you
everything you wanted.
I gave it to you all,
I gave it to you...
- Not quite, sh, sh,
sh, sh, sh, not quite.
You left out a vital
piece of information
and I'm not sure why.
- I don't know what you're...
What are you doing?
- I asked you for a list of
every single Biocorp employee.
- Okay, okay.
- And what did you give me?
Everybody in the U.S.?
- Wait, um...
- Why would you do that?
- Because I just
wasn't thinking clearly
and you're always
holding a gun to my head
and you didn't ask me
exactly what you wanted.
Okay, okay, okay.
- Well, I need everybody.
So do you understand
what I want?
- Okay, yes, yes, yes.
- Then get it for me, Kyla.
- Okay, I can do that.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
- Did I ever tell you, Kyla,
that you really remind me
of somebody I once knew?
- No.
- She had beautiful
eyes, just like you.
Smile that could
light up a room.
But she's not here anymore
because of you people.
- Okay.
Okay.
- How long, Kyla?
- Okay, it's coming.
It's coming right now.
Okay, just give me one,
just give me,
okay, that's all.
Okay,
it's coming out, okay?
Okay.
These are all of the Biocorp
employees in the world.
Tokyo, London, and Paris,
you have everything now.
It's in your hands, that's it.
I gave you everything
you wanted.
That's it.
- So there's nobody
missing from this list?
- No, no.
I promise, this is it.
I promise.
- I believe you.
You wouldn't lie
to me, would you?
- No.
No, no, I told you, I told you.
I told you.
You can trust me.
- Sorry Kyla, just can't
take the risk anymore.
- Commander.
- Our volunteer's
ready to go, sir.
- There's a change of plans.
- Sir?
- The president demanded
that we no longer waste time,
instructed me to
send my best soldier
to hunt down and kill
these three traitors
if they are still alive.
- I'll complete this mission
for Biocorp personally, sir.
- Commander, I am
counting on it.
- You're dismissed, get out.
- So I believe he shot that girl
because he knew she
would be disconnected
and safe in 27 days.
- I agree with that logic.
I think they must
all still be alive.
- You must find them.
- And then?
Yes sir.
- Son, is it ready?
- Yes, sir.
- Well give it to him.
- Thank you.
- What's this?
- I'm assuming they did what
they were supposed to do.
This will allow you to find
every member of
the Biocorp family.
- Chip locator?
- Well, we'll see.
Young man, does this work?
- Working perfectly, sir.
- Yes.
Commander, we are pulling
you back in 24 hours.
If you don't accomplish
your mission by then,
don't bother to put
yourself to sleep.
Understand?
- Understood.
- Good luck.
Let's start this
process, please.
(Dramatic orchestral music)
- Thomas,
hello, please call
me back, okay?
We've been,
we've been calling
you for hours.
All right, please call me.
- I hope he's okay.
- Yeah.
- Maybe he just needs
time alone, you know,
after everything that happened.
- I didn't go run and hide.
Son of a bitch.
- Nico, everyone
mourns differently.
- Yeah, but he could
have at least called me.
Where the hell have you been?
- I've been talking
care of things
that need to be taken care of.
And getting a little
drunk on the way.
- Where did you go?
- I killed Kyla.
- Who?
- An infertile Biocorp employee.
- Thomas you can just go...
- Why not?
She had information we needed,
now I have it.
And she understood.
- What about second chances?
- There's no second
chances anymore, Nico.
- What's this?
Huh?
- That's the name and
address and next of kin
of every Biocorp employee
in the whole wide world.
- How many people
are on this list?
- 1,980.
- Dear God.
Thomas, there's no way
we're gonna convince
that many people of anything.
- I'm not trying to talk
anybody into anything anymore.
- What do you mean?
- What he means, Jenny,
he's talking about killing
all of these people.
- What?
- What, are you a
mass murderer now?
Is that it?
- You know what?
I haven't been here
long enough to hear
your two guys' plan, but if
it's any better than mine,
I'm all ears.
- Well you know,
any plan is better
than killing 2,000
people, Thomas.
- Those people on that list,
they deserve to die.
They don't deserve to be,
are you kidding me?
Have you forgotten
what they did to us?
- What they will do.
- What?
- They haven't done
anything yet, Thomas.
- But they will.
- Oh God, so wait,
you're the judge,
the jury, and the
executioner now?
Is that what you want?
- You're judging me again?
- Yeah.
Talking down to me because
I got slightly more
blood on my hands than you do?
No, I've never quite
been able to get up
to that Nico standard
as usual, no...
- I've never said that.
- No, I've let you down.
I'm not good enough for you.
I've never been
good enough for you.
- I've never done that!
- And I've never been good
enough for your sister either.
- You keep her out of this.
- What a surprise.
We're not gonna talk about her.
- Both of you just stop.
- Listen, Thomas, we don't
have the time or the resources
to reach out to all these
people on the globe.
- Then we wait for a time
when everyone on that list
is in the same place,
at the same time,
which isn't as hard
as you might think.
Don't you worry, buddy,
I got it covered.
- You need to stop drinking.
Gimme that drink, that's enough.
- I haven't had nearly
enough to drink.
And that is still a good plan.
- What about this
butterfly effect
you always talk about, huh?
That's 2,000 people.
That's a lot bigger than
what you're talking about!
- I don't know, but
isn't it worth trying?
Just think about it, guys.
Please for a minute,
think about it.
If everybody on that list
goes, Biocorp is gone.
It doesn't exist.
Our home is safe.
We can go home and we
can toast to a world
without genocidal
criminals at our doorstep!
- You're calling them genocidal?
- Absolutely.
- And what does that make you?
- A goddamn hero.
Jenny please,
wait, Jenny.
The names on this list,
all the information
is enough to save
the whole world
and all we have to
do is execute it.
That's it, please.
- Look, I am not killing
2,000 people, Thomas.
- But it will save 6,000,000,000
so what does it matter?
What is there to think about?
This is a no brainer.
- It's a coward solution!
- It's simple statistics, Nico.
- You need to sober up.
- It will save Lauren.
It will save Lauren.
Do you get that?
- Do you know what
the professor said?
We cannot change the past.
- I'm not trying
to change the past.
I'm trying to fix our future.
- That's this future, Thomas.
What we experienced
was the future, okay?
What happened, happened.
- No, no, cause we're here
and we're changing things
all the time, every minute.
- Yes, I know we're
changing things.
We're changing the
future, not the past.
- You know that
for sure, do you?
You don't know that.
So you won't even try?
And you?
Then I'll do it alone
and I'll save us.
- I'll save us all.
- So smart.
You're really smart,
you know that Thomas?
- Thomas!
- You're so smart.
- What?
- We all lost her.
All of us.
- Yeah, but you know what?
We've got a chance to save her
and he chooses not to.
Look at him standing
there staring at me,
looking at me like
I'm the coward.
- Stop, stop it!
She wouldn't want
you to do this.
Stop it, you're
both best friends.
You forget about that?
- Yeah, I've forgotten.
You know what else, Jen?
Doesn't really matter what
Lauren would have wanted.
She's not here anymore, is she?
- He's gonna be okay.
He needs to sober up.
- I don't know, I don't know.
We're losing him.
- I think we already lost him.
- You know what, babe?
You know what the sad thing is?
I can't even say he's wrong.
- Maybe we can't save the world.
Maybe it's not a possibility.
We just have to save
as many as we can.
- I already lost my sister.
And now this.
No, no.
- He's the one that
we have to save.
Don't give up on him.
He's talking out of love.
- They told me you
were still here.
- Where else would I be?
- What is it?
What's wrong?
Is it the rebels?
- I was thinking about Jack.
- Jack?
- Yeah.
You know it's been
like 20 years now.
You realize that?
- I know he meant a lot to you
and yet you never
talk about him.
- I think about him a lot
more often than you realize.
- Well you think these men,
these ones who
traveled from the past,
you think they killed him?
- I think,
it makes perfect sense.
- I've seen that look
in your eye before.
Think before you act.
- You know something?
The last thing in the
world I need right now
is a lecture from you about
how I'm supposed to act
or what I'm supposed to
do because I already did
everything I could
the way you wanted.
- What I want?
I see you don't want a child.
You want us to die out.
- I abused my power.
I trifled with my power.
I did everything I
could in my power
to get what you wanted.
- You're right.
I'm just, I'm just trying
to help you do what's best
for all of us and part of that
is what's best for you and me.
- I'm trying.
We did this once before.
You almost died.
Forgot about that?
Listen, I,
I want to have a child.
Of course I do.
I just don't want to lose
you in the process, okay?
- Excellent, this'll be the
easiest hunt of my life.