Previously, on Dystopia.
- Track the microchip.
Find Nico and come home.
- My son.
I love you.
- See how even Travis
gets nervous at the
thought of death.
- She died trying
to save your life.
She never gave up, so stubborn.
- The names on this list.
All the information is enough
to save the whole world,
all we have to do execute it.
- I'm not killing
2,000 people, Thomas.
- Then I'll do it alone.
- I will use it to go back and
change things for the better.
- The greatest
evil is not done now,
but it is conceived and
ordered, moved, seconded,
carried, and communicated
in clear, carpeted, warmed
and well-lighted offices by
quiet men with white collars
and cut fingernails and
smooth-shaven cheeks,
who do not need to
raise their voice.
They are the focus of
evil in the modern world.
- Today, Nobel Peace Prize
winning Biocorp made history
by administering
the cure for cancer,
available to the enter
world's population
in exchange for their
voluntary enrollment,
compulsory enrollment
in the ID chip program,
which allows for increased
population security.
Biocorp CEO stated,
in time, we understand
that the only thing worth
fighting for is family,
and today is a day
when we must decide
to fight for what's right
or roll over and die.
That's all for tonight.
- We're all clear.
- Thank you.
Come here, babe.
- Was it a good news day?
- I don't know baby, we're
gonna have to wait and find out.
- What's going to happen now?
- I don't know, but things
are going to change.
- Mrs. Adams.
- Yes.
- I'm David Johnson
from Biocorp.
Both of you come with me.
Now!
- Okay, come on.
- Yeah, babe, you see,
Thomas has the list
so we can't warn
everyone ahead of time.
- He's not gonna go
through the entire list.
Plus, the police would
catch him here in this time.
- What's that?
- Why is this going off?
- Is that your tracker?
- Yeah, David
programmed it for me.
- Oh, well we can use
this to find Thomas.
- No, someone else is here.
- Babe, but no, that's
Thomas right there.
- No, there's a fourth signal.
Maybe it's David.
- No, you and I know
that's unlikely.
- Well if it's not
David, it's not friendly.
And whoever it is,
they are moving fast.
- We need to
get outta here then.
- Wherever we go
they're gonna track us.
- Yeah, well let me think, okay?
All right so, Thomas said
that everyone on that list,
that they're from
all over the globe.
So, uh...
- So you think he's
gonna fly everywhere?
- No, it's too slow.
I know.
- What?
- If you don't have a
way to go to everyone.
- You bring everyone to you.
- Exactly, he's trying to attack
everyone at the same time.
- I have an idea.
- What?
- David, he put an
AI on my tracker.
- Ah, good boy, David.
- We can have the AI, it'll
link over to the computer system
and we can have
internet in this time.
Okay, moment of truth.
Computer, do you
have internet access?
- Yes of course, what would you
- like to see?
- All right.
Adam, pull the database for
any upcoming Biocorp events.
- I have accessed
the public calendar
for Biocorp, there's a
staff gala this Friday,
would you like the details?
- Yes.
Bingo, there it is,
everybody on the list.
- Wow, we gotta move.
- You know it's a good thing
I went back and you stayed.
I never could've
built that thing.
You're very versatile,
you know that?
You having doubts?
Hey, I get it.
I mean, of course you are, you're
not some kinda psychopath.
If you weren't having doubts,
then I'd be worried about ya.
This is a serious
move, my friend.
I mean, not like what you've
already been doing isn't,
but this, this is the next step.
This is where you've
been heading all along,
and it's been a dark
road the whole way.
Have you thought
about how many people
are gonna be there tonight?
I mean, really thought about it?
People with families,
with children.
2000 people with
hopes and dreams
and you're gonna turn
'em al into corpses
in the span of a second.
You know what 2000
people is, Thomas?
- Shut up.
- Do you?
It's 0.0022%
of how many are gonna get
killed in the riots of 2021.
It's 0.000029%
of the population of this world,
all of whose futures are
being determined here,
now, by you.
So you push that button
and don't even pretend
you've gotta think about it.
I mean hey, let's
not kid ourselves,
what you're
doin' is, a horrible thing.
You're already a
murderer buddy, but this,
this makes you a butcher.
What you do tonight
will haunt your dreams
for the rest of your life.
- Stop.
- So really at this point,
there's only one thing
you gotta ask yourself.
How much is your
sleep really worth?
One horrifying act
for the future of all mankind,
and for her.
- I guess if he's
talking from your head,
that makes me your heart.
You can't escape your fate.
Maybe it's our time to bow out.
Everything and
everyone has its time.
The only tragedy
is, we missed ours.
I'm going to see
you again, my love.
And when I do,
I wanna recognize your face.
Don't save me and lose yourself.
- Yeah, yeah I'm on my way
from work right now, actually.
- Yeah, I know...
- Excuse me, officer.
- Oh hey, yeah
man, what's goin' on?
- Could you tell me
where Calley Avenue is?
- Calley Avenue?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, actually
if you head over.
- I love these old antiques.
- I need you to hear me out.
- What?
- We need to stop Thomas.
- I-I-I know that, baby.
- No, no, no, we need
to do whatever it takes.
- What do you
mean, whatever it takes?
- We can't let him
kill all those people.
- I know, but I'm not
gonna kill Thomas!
Okay, I'm not playing this
kill or be killed game.
- So what, you're gonna try to
talk him down off the ledge?
I mean, have you seen him?
- Yeah, I saw him,
baby, just, just,
you know what, just stop.
Let me just talk
to him first, okay?
- Talk to him, Nico you are not
the one he wants to talk to.
- All right, you're right.
All right.
- Last chance to
change your mind.
- I don't wanna change my mind.
- Bye.
- Well, I guess you're
really gonna do this then.
- Yeah, it looks that way.
- Is he goin' to work?
- Yeah, workin'
hard for his family.
- Reminds me of someone I know.
- Still never fixed it.
Man.
Sorry, sis.
- Who the hell are you?
- Look, look, look...
- Where're you taking my baby?
- No, listen, look,
mom, mom, mom, listen.
- Help, somebody help me!
- No, look, mom, mom, mom,
look, okay, look, I'm your son.
I know it's hard to
believe, it's me, Nico.
Look, I broke my arm
in a baseball game
with Jimmy Fink, okay?
I used to ice cream, in a
special bowl, with bananas.
Do you remember, when
I was four, okay.
- We don't have much time.
- Okay, listen, I'm
gonna let you go, mom,
but you cannot scream,
do you understand?
Do you promise?
Okay.
- Who are you people?
You look so much like...
- I know, I know, I
need you to focus, okay?
Okay look, I'm your
son, I'm all grown up.
This, this is my wife,
Jenny, from the future.
- Hi.
- We're here to save Lauren.
- What?
- Something horrible happened
to her in the future.
Okay, we have a
chance to save her,
if you let her come with me.
- It's not possible!
- Yes, listen, you
have to believe me.
Listen, she deserves to
live a good, full life.
- What, what happened to her?
- If you help us,
she'll still grow up
to be a beautiful woman,
marry the man of her dreams,
have kids, have a family.
But if you don't help us
mama, she's gonna die.
- I don't understand,
you are at school,
and now you are so old.
- It's been a long time.
- My son, my son,
even if I believe you,
how can I let you
take my little girl?
- Don't hurt my baby.
- Believe me,
we're here to save Lauren.
We're here to save Lauren, okay?
- Nico, we have to go.
- Okay, listen mom, Lauren's
gonna be safe, okay.
You need to cherish your
life with your husband,
and your son.
- What did you do to her?
Did you drug her?
- Listen mom, I gave
her something to sleep.
Okay, I just gave her
something to sleep.
- I can't let her go, no!
- Listen to me, she is my
best friend in our time.
She looks just like you,
your eyes and everything.
Nico.
- Okay, okay, look, okay,
promise me you can't tell dad.
He will not understand
if you tell him.
- This is too much,
this is not happening.
This is a lot of information.
I cannot even process
all what's happening now.
- Don't you feel it,
that he's your son?
- I know this is real, and I
can feel that you're my son,
but, yes, take care of her.
- I will.
- Nico, we have to go.
- I know babe, just
give me a minute.
- Please hurry.
- I will, I promise.
Take her to the car.
- Take care of her.
You grew up to be
a fine-looking man,
and your wife,
she's so beautiful.
- Yes, she is beautiful.
- What happened, what's
wrong, what's wrong?
- Mom, I have to
tell you something.
Where I'm from, you're not
in the future with me...
- But I'm here now, I'm with
you, I'll always be with you.
I'm your mother.
- Listen, you really
were the best mother
in the entire world,
the best mother.
- You always say that to me.
- Come on, Nico.
Guess you really
always were beautiful.
- Mom, you can come with me.
You can take care
of Lauren with me.
- But, who will be your
mother, here and now?
Who's gonna take care of you?
Who's gonna be there when
your father cannot be there?
I can't leave him,
I have to stay here
with you and your father.
- I heard that there are women
outside the city that
are still fertile.
They have a natural
immunity to the virus
that those inside
the city don't.
- I have to go now.
No, mom, no!
No mom!
- Are you hit?
- No, my mom's hit.
- Nico, you have to leave her.
Stand up, you have
to run, leave her.
- No, no.
- Nico.
- I don't normally do house
calls, but who's first?
- She is, doc.
How close?
- We have time.
- Doc, can you do
this fast, or what?
- I have no choice, let me see.
All right, this will
numb the area, okay?
- Okay, that sounds
like a good idea.
- It'll be fine.
- Okay.
- Don't look, don't
look babe, it's good.
- Jesus.
- No, it's okay babe, it's okay.
- Okay, all right.
- It's okay babe, no don't
look, don't look, don't.
You're doin' fine,
you're doin' just fine.
- Well come on, come
on, let's go, let's go.
- I've seen it, looks ordinary.
- We don't have time
for sightseeing, Doc.
- Yes, of course.
All right.
- It worked, but
he's getting closer.
- Stitch her quick
then, stich her quick.
- There's a bandage, okay.
Your turn.
- No, forget about it
doc, just forget about it.
- If you flinch, I could sever
a blood vessel or a tendon.
- Look, I'm not gonna
flinch, just do it.
- Okay, hold him still.
- Come on, let's go!
- Do not move.
You can't be still.
Almost there.
- And he's almost here.
- Where's the chip?
- I've got the chip,
it's in really deep.
- Go baby, go, go check
on Lauren in the car.
- What?
- Go to the car.
Go to the car and
check on Lauren, do it!
Do it, come on, it's
there and let's go.
- Almost there okay,
I'm almost there.
- Uh, come on Doc, come on Doc!
- Got it, I've got it.
Hey, I need to patch you up.
- Not enough time.
- You okay?
- What, oh yeah.
- You're just having a dream.
- Yeah.
- A dream.
- What?
- Oh, I had a nightmare.
- What, about the kid?
- Sort of.
- What do you mean, sort of?
- Well it started off that way
and then Thomas showed
up, and the kid, he...
- And it ended the
way it always does.
- Yeah.
Babe, he wants her.
- No, he doesn't, that's...
- Yes he does,
- he wants to hurt her.
- He doesn't, he doesn't.
- We gotta get her
somewhere safe.
- She is safe, it
was just a nightmare.
- No, we gotta protect her.
- We will.
- From Thomas.
- Thomas would never do anything
to hurt her, you know that.
- I'm afraid I don't, babe.
- Dammit.
Still got you.
(tense, suspenseful music
- Ow.
- You're still alive.
- Yeah, still ticking.
- Hi.
- And who is this little
person at my door?
What's your name, young lady?
- My name's Lauren, do you
have any apple juice, please?
- Yeah, come on in, we'll
what we can do for you.
- Thank you.
- Come on, I'll take you.
- Ow.
- Still sore?
- Yeah, it's all right.
- I should sew it up.
- Please.
- Well you managed not
to wreck your arm completely.
- Not that he didn't try.
- So who is your little friend?
- That's my sister.
- If you don't mind me
asking, where are you?
- My younger self,
I'm at home, with my father.
- What about your mother?
Things are getting more
and more complicated.
- You have no idea.
- What, what's the big secret?
- In the future, where I
come from, you saved my life.
His too.
- It's true.
- How'd I do that?
- We reconnect, but I
shouldn't tell you too much
about your own life.
- Well I'm glad to know
that I'm still around then.
- Anyway, I just
wanted to thank you.
You are one of the bravest
people that I ever meet.
- Well, it's the least
I can do for the man
that saved my father's life.
- Dad?
- Oh, come here, son.
We have some guests.
- You didn't tell
me you had a son.
- I mean, why else do I
have all those juice boxes?
This is Travis, Travis,
these are my friends.
- Hell Travis, I'm
Nicholai, you can call me Nico.
- Now go on and
play with Lauren, okay?
- Huh?
- She's staying here for
a bit, it's all right.
His mother passed away two
years ago in an accident.
He's all that I
have left of her.
Thanks to you, we have
more time, years perhaps.
And for that, I
am ever grateful.
- So he's doing well?
- He's healthy, and he has
a positive outlook on life.
And knowin' that
I have 30 years,
he'll probably still outlive me.
And poor Travis
is stuck with me.
- That's a good thing, Doc.
Spending time with
family's important.
- Yes it is, and Travis
is a full-time job.
Something wrong?
- No.
- You sure, babe?
- Um-hm, yeah, I'm fine.
- Thomas has one of these
trackers too, as I recall.
So where is he?
- Oh, he's, he's changed.
- We think that he's planning
something, something terrible.
- Something like what?
- I can't tell you right now.
- Well, whatever it is,
let me know if I can help.
- Actually, I do
need your help, Doc.
- No.
- I need you to
watch her for me.
- Oh course.
- You see something,
something bad happens to her
in the future, and we're
trying to prevent that.
- Is that what changes Thomas?
- Hm?
- He spoke of Lauren last time.
- Yeah I guess.
- Look, I'll watch over her
like she's one of my own.
- Are you sure, we don't
wanna inconvenience you.
- We could...
- Baby, it's just for now.
- I don't wanna pile
anything extra on him,
we should just take her and...
- Look, I understand,
if you don't stop Thomas
from whatever it is, it'll
only make matters worse.
- That's just it,
we gotta get goin'.
Is that Thomas?
- It's hard to say,
there's two signals
and they're getting closer to
each other, we have to go now.
- Wait, wait, wait, Nico.
Good luck, okay, and
don't worry about her,
she's in good hands.
- Thanks, Doc.
Let's go, babe.
Hey, what was that about?
- What?
- You look like you saw a ghost.
- He gave his life for you,
I wasn't sure if I
should say anything.
- I know but...
- His son, Travis, he doesn't
turn out quite so well.
It's nothing, okay just...
- Hey, hey, you sure?
- Yeah, I was just
caught off guard.
Let's go.
- All right.
Wish I could go back and
destroy that machine.
- Babe, none of this is your
fault, you know that, right?
- If I wouldn't have
built the machine,
none of this would've happened.
- You give people
a fighting chance
at something that
they never had before.
- There're gonna keep
sending people back after us,
don't you get it?
- What're you saying?
- What I'm saying is,
we need to get home now,
more than ever.
I've gotta rebuild the machine.
- Then you'll rebuild it.
- I, I can't
do it without Thomas.
- Then we'll convince Thomas,
after we stop him
from killing everyone.
- Right.
- Wait, wait, stop.
- Babe we can't, we
can't, no, babe, we don't...
- Okay, okay, everything's
gonna be okay.
- It hurts.
- Nico, call an ambulance.
- My baby!
- What's your name,
what's your name?
- Carmen.
- Carmen, okay, I need you
to breathe, Carmen okay,
stay with me, I'm
not gonna leave you.
- All right.
- You're not gonna be
alone, just relax, okay.
- Okay, the ambulance is coming.
Babe, you know we can't stay.
- Nico, I'm not
leaving her, I can't,
and you know why.
- No, no, no, we have to go.
- No, you need to go,
just go without me.
Find Thomas, I'll be right
behind you, I promise.
I'm meant to be here.
- Okay, okay.
- I love you.
Okay, okay, Carmen, I
need you to breathe, okay.
What's your baby's name?
- Kadence.
- Kadence, baby Kadence right?
You know how lucky you are?
- Do you, do you
have any children of your own?
- Not yet, one day.
- One day.
- Hey how you doin'?
- Good, and you?
- Good, good, good, did you get
into the Biocorp Ball tonight?
- Yeah, of course.
- You got an invite?
- Yeah, right here.
- Okay so I need that,
and your clothes.
- Good one, Arnie.
- Get out of the car,
give me the invite, man.
Come on.
Take your jacket off.
You work for Biocorp?
- Yeah.
- Well you really shouldn't.
- Come on, come on, come on.
- We didn't find any downside.
From all the research
that we've done, sir,
we have had absolutely
nothing goin' on,
but what I'm talking about
is we need to make extra sure
before we go in front of the FDA
or any of the other
approval boards...
- That's exactly...
- Senator, I'm so sorry.
- Oh, that's all right.
- But I just wanted
to shake your hand.
- Hello.
And Robert, I didn't expect
to see you again so soon.
What a bonus that you're here.
- Yeah, it's good
to see you too.
- Enjoy the party.
- There's a possible intruder
in the maintenance area.
Sir, this area's off limits.
- I'm sorry?
- I said sir, this
area's off limits.
- Okay, I'm
sorry, I'm not from here.
I was just looking for a
place for a cheeky cigarette.
- Sir, you're gonna
have to come with me.
- Yes, of course, please.
- Sir, this area's off limits.
- Yes, I'm sorry gentlemen, I
was looking for the bathroom.
- It's just off the main
entrance, it's this way.
- Ah, it is, well I will
just go straight there.
- We'll escort you.
- Please, lead the way.
- Can I see your
invitation, please?
- Yes of course, I've
got it right here.
- May I help you, sir?
- Hi, I'm here for
the Biocorp event.
- Sir, the main entrance
is around to the front.
- Oh I'm with a special
group within the company
that's here to put on a
special surprise tonight.
- Well do you have a
regular invitation, sir?
- No.
- Then I'm afraid I
can't let you in at all.
- Well I'm afraid
that I outrank you
in every conceivable
way and I am coming in.
- Sir, please leave the
premises immediately.
- Or what?
- Or I'll have you
arrested for trespassing.
- Then I guess you
better arrest me.
- Okay, give me one
big push, all right?
Come on try it,
you're okay, you're okay.
- I can't do it!
- Yes you can, yes you can.
I can't do it!
- You're doin' good, you're
doin' good, okay, look at me.
You're doin' a great job.
- I can't!
- One big push, okay.
- No!
- Okay, huh?
- Yes you can,
- keep on goin'.
- I see it, I see it.
- You're almost there.
- Come on,
- yes, there you go.
- No!
- Nice and big one,
come on, let's go.
- Yeah, yeah, here you go,
here you go, here you go.
Here you go, that's it.
Congratulations.
- Baby girl, congratulations.
- Cute little baby girl.
- She's beautiful.
- Wow.
- Aw, she's beautiful.
Trust me, I got the
better end of this deal.
I have to go, good luck, okay.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you, doctor.
- Excuse me.
'Cuse me.
- I missed you.
- What're doin', baby?
- I did what I have to.
- I came here to save you.
- No, no, I'm
trying to save you.
- No, this isn't the way.
- Please, let me do this,
otherwise I can miss you.
- Do you trust me?
- Yeah.
- Do you love me?
- Oh,
I do, I love you, I've always
loved you, always loved you.
- Trust it will be enough,
we'll see each other again.
- Honorable members
of the council,
it is my great privilege
to address you today
with a body of findings,
even if I do not...
- We warned you.
- Ladies and gentlemen, we
have a special guest tonight.
It's my pleasure to introduce
to you, Senator Jim Williams.
- Thank you, thank you all.
We're not quite sure where
Bob Tinker is right now,
but if it's all right with
you, I'll do the honors.
You have had a wonderful
and successful year
here at Biocorp.
Your hard work has
made the company
as powerful and
proficient as it is today.
But now, I have had
the honor of being
one of the prime architects
in the establishment
of a new government
contract with Biocorp.
The goal is that you, Biocorp,
will rid the entire world
of crime within
the next 10 years.
- Thomas, where are you?
Thomas, Thomas, Thomas.
Oh Thomas, thank god it's you.
- Nico, what're you doing here?
- What am I doing?
I'm here to stop you from
doing something horrible.
- How do you know about that?
- Thomas man, we're not
idiots, we figured it out.
- You probably figured out you
can't stop it either, Nico.
- Oh god.
- Nothing can stop it now.
- No.
- And in the name of God, Nico,
why would you
wanna stop it, huh?
Look at these people, they're
murderers, mass murderers,
every single one of 'em.
- No, no, they're innocent.
- Lauren was innocent!
- Look, Lauren wouldn't
want you to be doing this.
- Yes she would Nico,
she'd want me to kill a few
to save a billion,
you know she would!
- Do you want that on
your conscience, do you?
- It's bigger than us, Nico,
it's bigger than me and you.
Okay so just go, let
me do this, go, go.
- And what're you gonna do, huh?
It's a bomb, isn't it?
- It doesn't matter what it is!
- It's a bomb, isn't it?
- Yes!
- Oh my god, please
Thomas, we've got Lauren.
- No.
- No, we can fix this.
- Stop it, stop it, stop it.
- Thomas, look at me.
- Look at me!
- Stop it.
- She's with the doctor,
- we can fix this.
- No, as a baby, right?
You went and got her as a
baby, Nico it's not the same.
Nothing is gonna
- change my mind.
- Please come, please come.
- No, you, you gotta
go, for me please, go.
- Okay, fine, if you
kill these people,
then you kill me too, I'm
not leavin' without you.
- Then I'm gonna kill
Jenny too, right?
'Cause she's in the building
somewhere Nico, right?
She's here, right, somewhere?
You gonna take that
risk with her life?
Don't waste your
time following me,
you'll never find that bomb
Nico, you haven't got the time.
- Thomas, Thomas!
Oh my god, where is it?
- Was that Thomas?
- Yeah, that was Thomas.
Oh my god, there's a bomb
in here, we need to find it.
- It could be anywhere,
Dane's here too.
- What was it, honey?
- A baby girl.
- And what's...
- Everything's okay.
- Okay, that's good,
that's so good.
Okay, we need to
get everyone out.
Okay, everyone,
everyone listen up,
- listen to me!
- Listen!
- There's a bomb in the
building, we have to leave.
Everyone listen to
me, there's a bomb!
Get outta here!
Get outta here, there's a bomb!
There's a bomb, get out!
- Okay, come on, we gotta go.
Move, move, move!
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
- Freeze, don't move!
- Look, look, look,
look okay, we're okay.
- Nico!
- Thomas.
- What have you done?
- Are you crazy?
- We had to stop you.
- Stop me, you, you just
totally ruined everything.
- Thomas!
- Nico!
- There's still time
Nico to fix this.
Tell me what you
did with the bomb.
- You let her go, I swear to
god I'm gonna kill you, man.
- You already killed us, Nico.
You killed me, you killed
Jenny, you killed Lauren,
you killed every single
person we ever loved.
And for what, for these people?
- Look, look, look I'll figure,
I'll figure something out,
just let her go.
- No, Nico, this is
kill or be killed.
Time to man up,
give me the bomb.
- Whoa, whoa, oh,
wait, wait, wait,
there's a guy with
a gun in there.
He just shot two officers.
He's goin' crazy, he's
shootin' everybody.
- What was that?
Sir, something's wrong.
- What do you
mean, what's wrong?
- His
brain activity's all wrong.
- What do you mean, wrong?
- His heart rate's slowing too.
- Can't anyone here
do anything right?
- Baby, baby, hang in there.
- Okay, I will, okay.
- No, no, no, no, no!
- You should go, go.
- You know they're gonna send
more people back, Thomas.
You know he's not the end!
I need your help.
- To do what, to fix it?
I was trying to fix it, Nico,
that's what I was doing!
- Not that way, not in that way.
We can rebuild the machine,
okay, I just need your help.
I need your help, I need you.
- You can find the cause of
the virus before it spreads.
- The cause of the
virus was in that room
and you let them get away!
- We, we can...
- We can what, we can wait
for Biocorp to send back
another guy to kill us?
Or send back a guy to kill our
families before we're born!
What're we waitin' for?
We're waitin' for nothin', Nico.
And don't you worry, I'm
gonna fix it my friend.
And I'm gonna ask you
for just one more thing,
and then we never have
to see each other.
When I fix it,
don't get in my way.
That's the one extra thing.
- No, no, Jenny, no!
- We have to stop him, Nico!
- No, Jenny.
- Get another chance.
- Jenny, let him go.
- His brain
activity is inactive.
His heart rate's flat.
- Is there any chance that
he is still alive in 2017?
- No sir, he's uh, he's dead.
- Prepare the clean
sweep protocol.
- Do we have the authorization?
- Prep the machines!
- Yes, sir.
- This whole thing has
spun outta control.
How many can we send in?
- The speaker says
that by hour's end,
they will have completed
enough chambers
to send 50 at a time.
- 50?
- Yes, Mr. President.
- All right, tell him
to send four waves,
soon as possible.
- Four, sir, are you aware
of the concern many have?
- I'm very well
aware of the dangers.
We may be causing
our own annihilation.
But to do nothing, would
mean the same thing.
- How do you feel?
- Still alive.
- Thankfully.
So now what?
- I don't know, build a time
machine and head back home.
- I still think we
need to stop him.
- He's way beyond
our reach, babe.
- He'll kill too many
people before we can
assemble a machine
or fix anything.
We need to stop him, Nico.
Dammit.
- What is it?
- Oh my god.
- Oh they didn't
even wait a day?
Are they close?
- No, thank god.
- Wait, why is it
doin' this, is it broken?
- I hope so,
because if it isn't,
they just sent a
shitload of people back.
- Think I'm going
to like it here.