Previously on Dystopia.
- Our only hope
lies with the Biocorp
scientists finding a
cure for this pandemic.
- We're talking about the
extinction of mankind.
- He murdered a
Biocorp employee.
This is your new target.
- Hit it.
- If this is right we're
talking about time travel.
- Let me get this straight.
I'm going to become the
president of the United States
and be responsible for
the demise of the planet.
- You we can go ahead
and release that.
- Find who killed my son.
- I feel like something's coming
and I may not always
be able to be here.
- Today Noble Peace Prize
winning Biocorp made history
by administering the
cure for cancer available
to the entire world's
population in exchange
for their compulsory enrollment
in the ID chip program,
which allows for increased
population security.
The scheme is said to be
the greatest single stride
in medical science
ever achieved.
However, activists have warned
that a chip so fully immersed
into our bodies has godlike
control, citing that
something that looks too
good to be true, often is.
- Okay get ready.
- Come on.
Come on.
- No not yet.
- Come on.
- Wait.
- Come on, call it.
- Okay now.
- No don't touch her.
- Screaming.
- Hello.
What do we have here?
When you speak you will say
only what I want to hear.
- Please help my friend.
- You will tell me only what
I want to hear and nothing else.
Do you understand?
Good girl.
Those machines, what do they do?
Why are those men
attached to them?
Hey, the machines,
what do they do?
- Leave her alone.
- You son of a.
- I told you, you do not say
anything I don't want to hear.
You must not know me.
But you can guess what
I'm capable of, can't you?
Now I'm gonna give
you one more chance.
The machines, what do they do?
- Go to hell.
- See your little
friend over there?
Would you like me to give
you proof of my resolve?
- I don't think drinking
more wine is gonna help.
- I'm not getting
through this without it.
Case and point.
- I hate guns.
- Well maybe you'd
learn to appreciate
them more if you
were in a gun fight.
- Maybe.
- Do you thinK
the boys are okay?
- I'm sure they are.
Nico will look after them.
And I seriously doubt
Thomas is gonna let
anything get in his way
of coming home to you.
- What makes you say that?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
- Oh of course you don't.
- What if it's just the
way it's supposed to be?
- What, Biocorp
at our doorsteps?
Our men in comas,
theoretically in another time.
Um yeah, I'm guessing no.
- No I mean the pandemic.
I mean maybe, maybe we're
all supposed to die off.
You know?
Be extinct.
It happened to the dinosaurs
and maybe it's just
happening to us.
- No we're not
going extinct, Lauren.
- What makes you say that?
- Because when people fight
for life there's always hope.
- Maybe we're just supposed
to bow out gracefully?
- Will you stop
talking like that?
I heard that there
are women outside
the city who are still fertile.
They have a natural immunity
to the virus that those
inside the city don't.
Their babies live for
more than a few minutes.
But they're just so afraid,
they keep it hidden.
Besides, dinosaurs don't have
the brain power to
solve this problem.
We do, they do.
They're just trying to scare us.
- Sir, they've activated
the emergency power.
- Which floor?
- Not sure, sir.
- Well find out!
- Sir!
- They're not up there.
They're underground.
Give me the plans for
sewage access tunnels.
- Sir.
- Alright, so Phillip
Edier is in charge
of the Biocorp soldiers
outside of our home.
- Yeah.
You were supposed to
stay with the girls.
- I was.
You don't understand,
they're gonna
cut the power, they're
gonna storm the building.
- There's a backup
generator in the apartment.
- That'll buy us
time, it'll also light
the apartment up like
a Christmas tree.
- Weapons?
- Naw, we got none.
- We should've stayed with
them and now we can't get home.
- We can, we just have
to wait for the window.
- The next window
everybody could be dead.
- Us too.
- No, no, no, guys,
we're gonna save them.
We're gonna save everyone,
we have no choice.
- I didn't make you
come here, Nico.
- You're right.
All you did was kill
a Biocorp soldier
and led them back to our house.
- I'm sorry, next time I'll
just roll over and die.
What else could I do?
- Are you talking
about when you killed
the soldier or when you
executed Jack Williams?
- We don't have time for this.
- You know he's right, there
is actually too much to do.
- No matter what
you have in mind,
we all have to be in a
state of induced sleep
at the time the machine in
our time runs out of power.
- Why?
When we tried to bring
you back, you were awake,
you went into arrest,
we almost lost you.
- That explains the seizures
I had before you got here.
- Best we figure you have to be
asleep to make the trip home.
- Well how much time do we have?
- Told them to wake
me up in four hours.
- How long before the
emergency power fails?
- About the same time.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
If they tried to cut
the power out before
we only have about four
hours left in the generator.
- Yeah but this is also assuming
that they don't breach
the building first.
- Right.
- So, if we aren't asleep
when they try to revive us,
we all die in cryostasis.
- Great.
So we've got about
four hours to change
the entire future,
otherwise we're all dead.
- Thomas, I'm willing to sacrifice
my life to save humanity.
- Ah you know what, Nico,
if it's all the same to you
I'd like to save the
world and get home.
- You know we need to
finish what we started
otherwise there's going to
be no home to go back to.
- So what do we do?
- Biocorp headquarters,
it's here.
- So the ID chip,
the prototype for it,
if it exists now that's
where it will be?
- Exactly.
So David and I, we're
gonna go there together.
- And do what?
- We're gonna find
it and destroy it.
- What am I doing?
- Find the young Phillip Edier,
just do what you have to do.
- Are you asking me to
kill somebody, Nico?
- No I, I can do it.
- No, no, no, it's
okay, I just want to
be sure we know what
we're talking about?
- He's outside of our door
in 2037 with an
itchy trigger finger.
So do whatever it takes
to protect my family.
So in three hours
and 30 minutes,
meet us back at the
medical hospital.
Don't be late.
- You hear that?
They're growing by the minute.
- Yeah there's a
swarm out there.
- We should think about what
we're gonna do when
they come in here.
It's just an old man.
Look.
- Open it, let him in.
- I lost my way in the
dark, may I come in?
- Of course, but hurry please.
- I saw the light
under your door.
- You want to have a seat?
Uh, sir, do you
want to have a seat?
- Oh that's nice, thank you.
It's just too much out
there, for we wrestle
not against flesh and blood,
but spiritual wickedness.
I must get back out there
and fight those demons.
- You know, maybe you
should just have a seat.
It's cold outside.
We have a blanket,
we could warm you up.
- Oh that's nice, thank you.
Thanks.
You know it's just too much
out there, for we wrestle
not against flesh and blood
but spiritual wickedness.
I must get back out there
and fight those demons.
- Do you want some tea?
It'll warm you up.
- Tea?
Yes.
- I think you should stay
here and get strong first.
He seems a bit crazy.
- Well the war did
strange things to people.
- How much time do you think
'til the power goes out?
- Um, I don't know exactly.
Probably a few hours.
- Enough time to get them back.
- I hope so.
- There we go.
Huh, alright,
this'll be the best
dressed we've been in awhile.
- Ah, it's gonna
be a little tight.
- And I am a thief, I'm
stealing things now.
- Come on Dave.
Alright here's the
Biocorp headquarters,
okay now when we go in.
- You know we really
probably should've
gotten suits if we're gonna
pretend to be bankers.
Which, by the way, I don't
really know about finances,
and I definitely don't know
anything about finances in 2017.
You know in the future they
shoot people who bother them?
They probably do it now too.
- David, David!
You're gonna blow our cover man.
- Okay, okay.
- Just relax, I got this.
- You got this?
You look like you're
in a boy band,
which does fit the time
period, but doesn't really
explain why you're going
in there looking like that.
- David.
- Okay, okay, okay, you
got this, you got this.
- I got this, alright?
Relax.
- Shouldn't you shave at least?
- Okay, okay, this is good,
this is good, this is good.
My friend's gonna die,
gonna be stuck in the past.
- Hello, how may I assist you?
- Ah yeah, hi what's your name?
- Monica.
- Monica, nice name.
- Thank you.
- I am a venture capitalist
and I need to speak
to someone about investing
in your amazing company.
- Sure, sure.
- Thank you.
- Crap!
You okay?
Alright.
Hey, word of advice kid,
football's on its way out.
Learn how to shoot a gun.
- Hello sir, how are you doing?
Sara Washington.
- Hey I'm great, uh Paul Little.
- Wonderful, right this way,
I'm gonna give you a
tour of our facility.
- Okay, that's
really nice of you.
- Oh it's my pleasure.
I just happen to believe
in Biocorp very strongly.
I have passion in
everything we do here.
- That's great.
- It really is a
wonderful company.
- That's really good to hear.
- Phillip.
- Huh?
- I'm afraid I can't
answer that either, sir.
- So, how am I suppose to invest
if you're not willing
to talk about anything?
There's plenty of
information about Biocorp
readily available to
serious investors.
- Oh serious.
What about government contracts,
can you tell me about that?
You know, up and coming
projects, new ventures.
- I'm afraid I can't
disclose any information
about our company's
R&D contacts.
- Alright.
- You must understand that many
are of a commercially
sensitive nature.
- Mm hmm.
- As I'm sure you can imagine.
- Yeah.
- I can tell you, however,
we have an entire floor dedicated
to R&D of various forms.
But as to who our
clients are, sir,
that's proprietary information.
- Well can I get a sneak
peak of the R&D wings?
No details, I just want
a quick look, that's it.
- Will you excuse
me for a moment?
I'll be right back.
- Right.
- I apologize about this, sir,
but asking questions
of a sensitive nature
has tripped our security
director's interest.
I'm afraid we'll have to detain
you for a short while whilst
we establish identity and
validate your queries as genuine.
I assure you that
these gentlemen
will keep you more than
comfortable as you wait.
- If you can come with us, sir.
Now.
- Hey guys can I tie my shoe?
I just gotta tie
my shoe real quick.
Okay, okay, see, not doing
anything, not doing anything.
Where is it?
Where's the chip, chip, chip?
Oh this is it.
Oh my gosh.
They're already in production.
This must be an earlier version,
this is way bigger than
the one in my body.
Hard drive.
Got it.
- We have a security breach.
- Let's go.
Copy.
Okay.
Come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Got it.
- Get me security.
- Hey they didn't shoot you.
- No, no, I'm good.
- That's good.
- How about you?
- You know I think I
would've been a good dad.
- Alright, tell
me about it later.
- Begin.
- You should just tell Nico.
- Tell him what?
I don't think my
brother would approve.
- He is your brother, exactly,
he just wants you to
be happy, he loves you.
- Jenny, the
emergency power is running low.
You have two hours remaining.
- You girls seem
worth fighting for.
You remind me of how my
wife used to look at me.
- Oh yeah, where is she?
- Heaven.
If you believe in
that sort of thing.
You know it's hard
losing the one person
that was made just for you.
- I think the power's going out.
- Ah that's just her,
she does that sometimes.
Well, I want to thank you ladies
for all of your hospitality.
Now it's time for me to go.
I need to get back out
there, there's something I'm
supposed to do but I just can't
quite remember what it is.
- Why don't you stay until
the main power comes back on?
I can make you more
tea if you want.
- It's good tea.
But my bladder's not as strong
as it used to be, I'm afraid.
- Oh come on, we have
a bathroom right there.
- You're too kind.
- Poor guy.
I couldn't imagine
loving Nico that long
and then just losing
him, you know?
- I'm sure he'll be okay.
You're survivors.
- Lauren I don't
want you to die here.
Nico would want you to
try to at least get out.
- Nico would want
me to stay with you.
- They're coming for him.
- They're coming for all of us.
Besides, where else would I go?
- Please, don't hurt me.
- Shut up.
Shut up!
All I have to do to save my
whole world is pull the trigger.
- I haven't done
anything, I'm just a kid.
- You will.
You will.
You are going to cause so
many people so much pain.
- I don't know what
you're talking about.
- But if I pull the trigger,
the ripples may make things
worse where I'm from.
The butterfly effect,
you see, we don't know.
Broad brush strokes,
they're too much.
The future, the future
needs a finer touch.
- I don't know what the hell
you're talking about
or who you are.
Please, please let me go.
- Shut up, Phillip, because
I'm gonna try and help you.
I'm gonna give you a chance
to do the right thing,
to make the right choice,
so that our future
really is in your hands.
- Please, my dad has money.
- I don't want your
father's money.
Don't you get that?
I want my future back.
- I don't know what the
hell you're talking about.
- Do you believe in time travel?
You will.
Because if I fail,
many years from now,
you and I are going
to come face to face
and you remember my face,
you take a good look,
because I won't have
aged a single day.
Look at my face.
- You're crazy.
- Where I'm from,
in a world you can't
possibly comprehend,
everything's crazy.
All hope is gone, because
people like you took it away.
And I'm not gonna stand here
and watch my future end.
But I am gonna stick
to the mission.
- What are you doing?
- I'm gonna give you a way
to remember me, real easy,
you look at my
face as I do this.
I'll see you again, Phillip.
- How much time do we have?
- Less than five minutes.
- Oh gosh.
Are you sure this is the
right medical facility.
- Yeah, it was here when
I was 10, broke my leg.
Lots of ice cream.
- David, Thomas should've
been here by now.
- Well, what if he.
- No, no, no, no,
he's fine, he's fine,
he can take care of himself.
- Alright, we need to
find someplace secluded.
- Why?
- Because we gotta go to sleep.
Which, by the way, really not
sure I'm gonna be able to do.
- I got an idea, follow me.
What is this place?
- It's a simulation center.
Yeah, doctor's used to
use these to practice on.
It's not creepy at all.
- Yeah.
Alright, what are we
looking for again?
- Chloroform or any good
anesthetic should do the trick.
- It's probably in there.
- Yes, yes, okay.
This is weird.
- What do we got, what
do we got, come on.
- I'll look over here.
Ah here we go.
- What do we got?
Perfect.
Okay.
- Come on Thomas, come on.
- We're running out of time.
- We can't leave Thomas, man.
- He could've put
himself to sleep already.
Look we can't wait for him,
otherwise we're gonna get stuck
here or we're gonna be dead.
- Fine let's get it ready.
If he comes, he comes.
- Yep.
- If not then we'll have to put
ourselves under and
hope he did the same.
- Okay.
- You're sure this
is gonna work?
- No, but it's the
only choice we got.
- Alright well try
it on me first.
- No, no, no, it's me first.
The girls know to
wake me up first,
that's why I'm on the clock.
- Well what if it doesn't work?
- Well then they won't
wake up you or Thomas.
- Well what so we're
here and you're dead?
- Or stuck here with you.
Either way this is the
only choice we got.
- Just do it on me first.
- No we can't do
it like that, Nico.
- I'm not letting
you risk your life.
- Look I'd risk my life
for you any day, okay?
- Look stop being dramatic,
just, let's do it
at the same time.
Let's go.
- Alright, alright.
Sorry, pal, can't argue
with you on this one.
- Dammit, David.
- Oh man I hate needles.
- Out of time.
Welcome back, David.
- Nico.
- It worked.
- No, no, no, no, no, not yet!
- Why!?
- He's, he's not asleep yet,
he's still waiting for Thomas.
- No, no, they're
here, they're here.
- We can't stay here.
- We have to give them
more time to put themselves
into stasis before we wake
them up or it'll kill them.
- What happened there?
- We got split up,
Thomas was supposed
to meet us, he never showed.
- No, no, no, no, wait look,
look, he's still alive,
his brain activity's still high.
- Okay where was mine
when we walked through?
- Just right here.
- Okay so that's obviously
where sleep patterns kick in.
We need to wait until
their brain activity
is where mine was
before we wake them up.
- What about Nico, is he okay?
- He's fine, he's
fine, so is Thomas.
We were all together,
we just got split up.
- Oh thank god.
I can't believe
you were in 2017.
- Yeah, yeah it's beautiful.
- That's crazy.
- Did you change anything?
- Nothing you want
to know about.
For all I know it
made things worse.
- Worse?
How would we know
if it were worse?
If you changed
something the ripple
would be part of our
present, always with us.
- Ripples indeed.
- Who is that?
- Don't worry about him, he
came in the blackout, he's fine.
What, what, what's so funny?
- It worked.
They did it, they
invented time travel.
And I'm the guy who got to go
and come back in one piece.
- I wouldn't rely on being
in one piece for too long.
They're getting closer.
- Can we move them?
- No they need to stay
hooked up to the machine.
- Then we need to wake them up.
- You can't.
- The power source
is almost out.
- Look we have to risk it.
Either the Biocorp soldiers are
gonna burst through the door
or the power's going out.
Either way, they'll die.
We have to pull them back.
- No, you'll kill them.
- Let go of me.
- No wait.
- No.
- Jen, Jen, just wait.
- No, let go of me.
- You have to wait,
give them more time,
he will find Thomas.
- Please, I can't lose Nico.
- You won't, Nico's a survivor.
But if you do this he is dead.
- They're on the floor above us.
- Okay, okay, okay, is
there another way out?
- Maybe through the
sewers, but I don't know.
- No, no, no, we're
not leaving them.
- Alright I'll stay, I'll
stay, and I'll wake them up.
- What happens then?
- Then we'll find you.
We can find you.
Look I swore to Nico I'd
keep you safe, both of you.
Please just go.
- I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, sorry, sorry.
- Where the hell were you, man?
- I was busy with
our mutual friend.
- Did you kill him?
- Where's David?
- He's gone.
- What do you mean gone?
It worked?
- He just disappeared
right in front of me.
- That's incredible.
- It's crazy.
- So we can go home.
- So what did you do with Edier?
- I'll explain later.
- No, no, wait, wait.
What'd you do?
- I gave him a
chance okay, Nico?
- You let him go?
- Nico, I'm sorry, okay, I
didn't want to kill him, Nico.
- Oh my god, Thomas.
- I'm sorry.
- What, you killed Jack
Williams like that, and then.
- Yeah and look how that
turned out for us, okay?
Remember the butterfly effect?
That doesn't work.
- Oh my gosh, Thomas.
- I know, I know.
- All you had to
do was kill him.
The siege is done.
- We don't know that, okay Nico?
He could've been replaced
by somebody worse.
Somebody that wanted to
bomb the whole building.
- Look Thomas we have
a little bit of time
to make a big impact
to avoid the future.
- I know, I know, I know,
but is that what you
did at Biocorp, huh?
No.
Let me guess, broad brush
strokes, it don't work, right?
Come on we know that.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, I
know, I remember that,
but come on man.
You killed Jack Williams
with no hesitation
and now you're trying
to do the right thing
because you think you
understand the butterfly effect.
- I didn't say I understood,
okay, I didn't say
I understood, I said
I gave him a chance.
I left him with such a lasting
impression of me that
he will never forget.
When he sees my face
in 20 years from now,
he is not gonna forget.
And he's gonna believe
in time travel, Nico.
He's gonna do the right thing.
- How do you know?
How do you know that?
- I don't.
- Do you know what he becomes?
Do you?
- No.
- And we won't know
until we go back.
- Okay so we should
just go back.
Or we can stand here
for another hour
and talk about it whilst
we leave the girls alone.
- Let's go.
- What is it?
- They've activated the signal.
They're getting ready to
put themselves to sleep.
Candles, blow out the candles.
Okay get ready.
- Come on, come on.
- No not yet.
- Come on, come on, come on.
- Not yet, Jenny.
- Come on.
- Wait.
- Come on, call it.
- Is this gonna work?
- I dunno, it worked for David.
- Well how do we know?
How do we know that
David just didn't
simply blip out of existence?
- We don't.
- Brilliant.
- It's now or never.
- Now, now.
- About time.
- No, don't touch her.
- Lauren!
- Hello.
What do we have here?
When you speak you will say
only what I want to hear!
- Please help my friend.
- You will tell me only what
I want to hear and nothing else.
You understand?
Hmm?
Good girl.
Those machines, what do they do,
and why are those
men attached to them?
Hmm?
Hey the machines,
what do they do?
- Leave her alone.
- I told you.
Now I'm gonna give
you one more chance.
The machines, what do they do?
- Go to hell.
- You see your little
friend over there?
Would you like me to give
you proof of my resolve.
- Phillip Edier!
- Can I help you, grandpa?
- Take a closer look
and remind yourself
of what you once knew.
- Lauren.
- It can't be.
I know you.
You called it the
butterfly effect.
You said you wouldn't change.
It's been 20 years and
I remember your face.
You haven't aged a day.
- Don't touch him.
Time travel.
- Please, she's going to die!
- Get that woman
medical attention.
- Sir.
- Stabilize her.
Well how does this
wonderful machine work, hmm?
Bring in a science team.
- Yes, sir.
- Emergency power
failing, system shutting down.
- Wait, you, leave her.
If you want your two
friends to survive,
you better tell me everything.
- Turn the power back
on or you get nothing.
- I'll just let her die.
- Go ahead, kill us all,
then you'll have no answers.
- Start talking.
- Power.
- Main power to the
building, turn it back on.
- Yes, sir.
- System power restored.
- Start talking.
- What is it you want to know?
- Those men, where are they?
Or rather when are they?
- Hey you can't sleep here.
Hey, I need some help.
Two guys, I think they're dead.
- Page Dr. Mangan.
- That's magnificent,
such potential.
- We're all though here, sir.
- She'll survive?
- She's as good as new.
- The boys are okay,
they miss you very much.
- You hear that?
They're gonna be okay,
you're gonna be okay.
How are you feeling?
- I'm okay.
- Time to wake up.
There you go, that's
it open your eyes.
That's it.
There you go, come on back,
come on back, you're safe.
Welcome back to reality.
- Where am I?
- You're in a hospital.
You were found unconscious.
You remember how you got here?
- What year is it?
- What year do you think it is?
- What are these for?
- Those are for
your own protection.
- Where am I?
- You're okay.
- I'm dreaming?
- Yes, you're dreaming.
But you have to wake up.
- I don't want to wake up.
I want to stay here with you.
- I want to stay too.
But you have to help Nico.
Wake up.
- No.
- Good morning.
- What is this?
- It's okay.
You've had a seizure.
- Why am I tied up?
Where am I?
- You're in the hospital.
- What?
- The doctor will be right here.
- Nico.
No wait, my friend Nico.
Hello?
- Can you tell me your name?
- Why am I tied down?
- You had a seizure.
This tattoo, it's
very interesting.
This bracelet, the material,
I've never seen
anything like it before.
So can you tell me your name?
- How long have I been here?
- Since last night.
You had a strong
tranquilizer in you.
So strong you're
lucky you're alive.
- I guess I over did it.
- You did this to yourself?
- Look, you wouldn't understand.
- I understand that you
and your friend are
both lucky to be alive.
- Where is he?
- He's safe.
- Excuse me Dr. Mangan,
you're needed in the other room.
- Okay get some rest.
I'll come back and
check up on you later.
- We didn't want to hurt anyone.
Such an unpleasant
waste of time.
We could all help each other.
We could help the world.
I'll guarantee your
freedom if you tell me what
your friends are up to or I
can just shoot you one by one.
- That's not necessary.
- Then speak up.
- We were just trying
to save the world.
- Is that all?
I'm listening.
- Mike, is it?
- Yeah um, Michael Smith.
- So where are you from, Mike?
- Uh Pennsylvania.
I uh.
- Your eyes blurry?
- Yeah.
- I'll get the
nurse to hook you up
with an IV, help
flush out your system.
- How much longer do
I have to be here?
- Relax, I need to find
out who you are first.
Speaking of.
- Michael Smith?
- What are you doing?
- Just trying to
figure out who you are.
Don't worry, we'll get
you back where you belong.
- We're trying to avert
the chipdemic virus
that has doomed our
planet to extinction.
- It's true, everything
he speaks of.
- Who are you anyway?
- He's harmless.
- I wouldn't say harmless now.
- Before you start
trying to save the world,
how many trips
have they been on?
- None.
- None?
Oh well that is
interesting and brave.
For all you know
there is no way back.
- I got back.
I got back.
- And did you have any success
in changing the future?
- I honestly don't know, I
don't know what they've done.
- What did you do?
- I don't know what changes
have been made if any.
We might not know
'til they get back,
we might never know.
Everything's in a
state of temporal flux
until the link we've
created is severed.
It's only when the tunnel is
closed that we'll actually
see the full effect of the
changes that were made.
- But you were in the past?
- I was.
- I want to go there myself.
- You could get lost forever
if you don't know
what you're doing.
- Well that's why you gotta
make things smooth for me.
- I can't assure that.
- If anything goes wrong, everyone
in this room is executed.
- What, what, what happens
if you get yourself
killed back there,
that's not our fault.
Spare the girls at least.
- Make it work and
you'll have no problems.
- It's not that easy.
- Then make it easy!
Or I'll make it hard,
beginning with her!