(SINGING) The Simpsons
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
(HORN BELLOWING)
(PLAYING DIFFERENT TUNE)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(HONKING)
D'oh!
(SCREAMS)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
Putting away groceries,
it's like
unwrapping presents
from yourself.
Fruit Roll-Ups for Bart.
Beer Roll-Ups for Homer.
(GASPS)
Burly? I bought
the wrong brand, Maggie.
I'll just
take them right back
to the store and...
Whoa!
Look at those
massive plaid
shoulders!
Look at that absorbativity!
I've gotta tell someone.
I came home
as quick as I could.
What's going on?
Watch what happens
when I spill
this blue liquid.
You pulled me
out of school
for this?
Absolutely. You're
about to get a lesson
in value.
And Burly's still
got soaking power.
Spill something else.
Mom, I believe you.
Spill it.
Hmm?
Ooh, Burly,
you're insatiable.
(LAUGHS WEAKLY)
Oh, Burly,
you're so rugged
and manly.
Marge, a bee almost
stung me today.
I felt the wind go
right by my ear.
(WHIMPERING)
Oh, it's okay, Homie.
The bee's all gone.
Mmm!
Fantasize, Marge.
Fantasize about Burly.
(CLICKING TONGUE)
(GRUNTING)
Hey, you're looking
at that spokes-jack.
Well, I can fantasize, too.
Hmm.
Ooh! Mama Celeste.
(PURRING)
You touch me
and I cut you.
Homer, I'll tell you
what I told Redford.
It ain't gonna happen.
(GROANS)
MARGE: "Dear Burly, comma,
I've never written to
a registered trademark before.
"Are you a real person
or just a composite?
Question Mark.
"In either case,
I would love
a signed photo.
"Sincerely, Marge Simpson."
(LAUGHING DEVILISHLY)
"Love"? (GASPS)
"Signed photo"?
Marge hasn't asked me
for a signed photo
in months.
Well, I'll show her.
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
Hello?
We have
a person-to-person call
for Marge Simpson.
Person-to-person!
(IN DEEP VOICE) Hello.
This is Chad Sexington,
the model for
Burly Paper Towels.
(GASPING)
How did you
get my number?
I don't know.
But I was quite moved
by your letter.
I'd love to meet
you and your family.
Shall we say dinner?
Oh, my goodness...
Perfect.
I'll be there at 7:00.
Oh, my God!
Dinner with Burly!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Playing a prankeroo, eh?
I was having
a private conversation
with my wife
in the guise of
Chad Sexington.
Do you mind?
(HUMMING)
So, how was your day?
Did anything
unbelievable happen?
Phone calls?
Things of that nature?
You're not
gonna believe it.
That paper towel lumberjack
is coming here
for dinner tonight.
Tonight?
Well, you better
get your hopes up.
I will.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(DOORBELL RINGING)
That's him!
Oh, my God!
Why, look.
It's Chad Sexington!
Hey, baby!
I'm that guy you like.
Barney? Where's Chad? I...
(LAUGHING HEARTILY)
Congratulations.
I feel ridiculous.
You mean I was just a prop
in some cruel joke?
Now you've done it.
You've really humiliated Mom.
It was hard on me, too.
I had to wear a suit.
Oh...
You're right. I've gotta
make it up to her.
I suggest
dinner and a show.
How about Benihana,
where dinner is the show?
(BOTH GRUNT DISAPPROVINGLY)
No, huh?
Walking to hell
and back again
I guess it was
a pretty funny prank.
I like the ones
where nothing
catches on fire.
Yeah. Nothing is
hurt except feelings.
Walking to hell
and back again
Okay. You've seen
our next performer
on Mike Douglas, Merv Griffin
and Art Linkletter's
House Party.
Please welcome Mesmerino,
the hip hypnotist.
Thank you.
Thank you very, very much,
ladies and gentlemen.
Let's see.
Who do we have here?
Well, what's the matter
with you, champ?
You couldn't find a date?
I didn't come here
to be heckled and
spoofed and whatnot.
Why did you come here?
Seriously though.
When I snap my fingers,
my friend,
you will be
a make-out artist.
Glayvin! That's a powerful...
(EXCLAIMS) Whoa!
Hold it
'cause it's different!
(DINERS EXCLAIMING)
(SMOOTHLY)
Hey, cupcake, listen good.
I want you
to swallow that gum
and meet me in the coatroom,
in five,
four, three, two, now.
(GULPING)
Whatever you say, Professor.
And back you go.
Ooh! Hey!
No, no, don't make me!
I don't want to go
back to the nothing!
I don't...
(GRUNTING)
(IN NORMAL VOICE) Oh, dear.
I've redorkulated.
Hey, smart move, Four-Eyes.
Sitting next to Skeletor here
makes you look like Hercules.
(HOMER LAUGHING)
Zing.
What's a "Skeletor"?
No, no, I kid.
But seriously,
it's very nice
to see a young man
take his father out
for a night of hypnotism
before he dies.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Actually, my father
died a long time ago.
(ALL EXCLAIMING IN SYMPATHY)
Okay. Is anyone here
not a downer? Anyone?
Do me! Do me!
(GIGGLING EXCITEDLY)
I am in your power.
Boss me around.
When I snap my fingers,
you will transform into
a famous historian.
Look at me!
I'm a famous historian!
Out of my way!
Thank you.
Now you are
Emily Dickinson.
Look at me!
I'm Angie Dickinson!
Out of my way!
Now you are a young boy,
uh, yourself
at 12 years old.
(IN BOYISH VOICE)
I'm 12 years old.
I'm with my friends.
It's a beautiful summer day
at the old swimming hole.
Oh, my God!
(SCREAMING)
Do something, Mesmerino.
Uh, yes. Yes.
(SIGHS)
That's better.
(SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING LOUDLY)
Dad, what's wrong?
We better
get him home.
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
There you go.
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(GROANING)
Hmm!
And Bart is set for the week.
(SCREAMING)
Oh, no.
Sorry, Mrs. S.
He was kind of
disrupting things at work.
Yeah. He ruined
naptime and quiet time.
Oh, Homie,
you poor thing.
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
Oh, cool.
He's still mental.
Yeah. My hunch is
he's struggling with some
sort of repressed memory.
Hmm. How do we
unrepress it?
Well, the Yaqui Indians
brew a special tea
that unlocks memories.
It would be a good excuse
to use my Yaqui tea set.
Well, is anything
coming back to you?
Oh.
(CHUCKLING)
There have been so many
classic Simpson moments.
I remember that time
I tried to jump
over Springfield Gorge.
I'm gonna make it!
LISA: No, Dad. Everyone's
sick of that memory.
Try to remember
back when you were 12.
Something frightening
must have happened.
Hmm. Twelve.
Well, I remember
I used to go hiking a lot
with these two guys.
It was one of
those lazy summer days
you thought
would last forever.
And to kill the boredom,
we sang.
(HUMMING)
ALL: Mister Sandman,
bring me a dream
Make him the cutest
that I've ever seen
Check it out, Fat Tony.
Those jokers think
they're The Cowsills.
And lots of wavy hair
like Liberace
You guys have blundered
into our secret tobaccy patch.
Wow! Is that
wacky tobaccy?
The wackiest.
Let's punch
and kick them!
(ALL GASP)
Not so fast.
(GRUNTING)
He's got a Daisy.
We better scram.
Eighteen more pumps,
that could break the skin.
Hey, thanks, Moe.
And that's how
a troubled young Moe
saved the day.
Moe, what are you
doing here?
What am I...
My bar is empty is what.
Why ain't you guys there?
We're trying to
uncover a hidden trauma
in my dad's childhood.
What? You mean
that time he wigged out?
Well, give me
some of that Indian
memory tea there
and I'll tell you
all about it.
(IN FUNNY VOICE)
Mmm! That's good Yaqui.
(CLEARS THROAT) Okay.
That night we camped out
under the stars.
(SIGHS)
Look at all them stars.
Bunch of lazy lights,
don't do nothing for nobody.
Hey, you know what
I'm looking forward to?
The future.
Have you heard about
this Internet thing?
Internet?
Yeah. It's the inner
netting they invented
to line swim trunks.
It provides
a comforting snugness.
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
Hey, what was that?
LENNY: That's that
nuclear plant
they just opened.
Yeah, that's your future,
busting atoms.
Can you imagine
us working there?
The whole Carl Crew?
Hey, I thought
we were called
Lenny and the Jets.
Hey, you're both wrong.
We're the
Moe Szyslak Experience,
featuring Homer.
I like the sound of that.
Friends forever?
ALL: Friends forever.
HOMER: Ow!
Ow! That hurts!
Man, we're stupid.
I hate you guys.
MOE: The next morning
we went out to the old quarry
to have a swim.
(WHISTLES) You guys really
gonna dive off of here?
Not me. I'm shaking
like a French soldier.
Yeah. I think I just
logged on to my Internet.
Only a moron would
jump into that...
Geronimo!
Oh, my God!
(SCREAMING)
And there's
your whatchamacall
repressed trauma.
I mean,
who likes getting muddy?
It's terrible.
Okay.
Let's go to Moe's now.
Wait a minute.
I remember falling
in the mud.
But I don't think
that's why
I've been screaming.
Fine.
Crap all over my theory.
Something else
happened in that quarry.
Something else.
Hey, what happened
to all the water?
Hmm.
Hey, there's
something blocking it.
Hey, come on.
(GRUNTING)
Come on, Homer!
We're going to Sears
to feel the bras!
What the heck is that thing?
(EXCLAIMING)
(SCREAMING)
You found a corpse
when you were 12?
(WHIMPERING)
No wonder you've
been so traumatized.
It's responsible
for everything
wrong in my life.
My occasional overeating,
my fear of corpses.
(SOBBING)
What I want to know is
what the heck was
that body doing there?
Maybe there's murder afoot.
Murder most foul?
Maybe.
You know,
if Dad never told anyone,
that body must
still be out there.
This sounds like a case
that only the Simpson family
can solve.
Oh.
Okay. Uh, well,
we'll just be going then.
Hey, you guys can
come with us.
No, no, no.
He said "Simpson family."
I mean, you know,
it sounded exciting.
But, you know,
we don't want to intrude.
Thanks for understanding.
Oh.
Oh, okay. Well...
I'll see ya.
HOMER: Bye, Moe.
(CHUCKLING)
Yep. The old quarry
is just a stone's throw away.
Stop saying that, Dad.
Never.
Hey, there's Mesmerino.
Seventeen seventy-six.
"How much is left
in my checking account."
HOMER: This is it.
This is the old quarry.
Maybe we should come back
in the daytime.
Someone's yellow
belly is showing.
Oh, sorry.
(RUSTLING)
(ALL GASPING)
Ah, geez.
Right in the eyes.
Chief Wiggum!
Who's there? How do you...
How do you know my name?
It's us, the Simpsons.
Oh.
I saw your car
by the gate and I...
Well, I thought
you might be lost hikers.
'Cause then
I could rescue you,
and be a hero.
And maybe
the city would give me
a coupon for
free guitar lessons.
So what are you doing here?
We're investigating
a possible murder case.
Oh. You mind if I tag along?
I'm kind of a crime buff.
If there's a body in here,
we'll drag it up.
(GRUNTING)
Heck. It's just
an old shopping cart.
Oh, and it's empty.
Put it back.
I don't want to
see it this way.
We'll never find the body
under all this water.
Water, eh?
Burly to the rescue!
CLANCY: Oh, that is so cool.
Hey! What's that over there?
Don't get excited.
It's just a skull-shaped rock
and a bunch of white sticks.
It's the body.
And someone has
eaten the flesh.
(GRUNTING IN ACCUSATION)
But whose body is it?
And who sent it
down that pipe?
Now do you believe
dead rats float, Lisa?
Yes.
Well, looks like
the end of the line.
That means our murderer
could be on
the other side of this hatch.
(SQUEAKING)
(GUNSHOT)
(EXCLAIMS)
What are you doing
in my corpse hatch?
Montgomery Burns,
you're under
arrest for murder.
Did I say corpse hatch?
I meant "innocence tube."
Then how do you
explain this?
I've been expecting
this day for 30 years.
In a way, it's a relief.
But in another way,
it's most unwelcome.
All right,
quit stalling, Burns.
Who'd you ice?
I'm afraid that skull
belongs to my dear friend,
Waylon Smithers Senior.
(GASPS)
Mr. Smithers' father!
But I did not murder him.
And I can prove it
with this film.
Ooh! A movie!
I call the couch!
(LAUGHING)
If you see only
one film this year that
proves my innocence,
make it this one.
(ALARM BLARING)
Why are these
numbers so high?
Why is that
red light flashing?
And what's that
alarming sound?
Smithers, get in here!
Smithers!
Sorry, Monty.
I was feeding Waylon Junior.
Will you put
that baby down?
There's something wrong
with the reactor core.
(ELECTRICAL BUZZING)
I better go in
and have a look.
No, Waylon Senior.
It could be filled
with atoms, and steam,
and other
nuclear bric-a-brac.
If this reactor blows,
the whole town is doomed,
including my son.
(GURGLING)
So, you're a baby, huh?
How's that
working out for you?
(POWERING DOWN)
He did it!
Look at your
heroic daddy in there
making funny faces,
falling to the floor,
shedding his hair,
lying perfectly still...
Oh, dear.
Sir.
Smithers Senior gave his life
to save the plant.
And since cover-ups
were all the rage back then,
I shoved his heroic corpse
down the sewer pipe.
I never told Smithers
the truth about his father.
Until tonight, sir.
(GASPS)
Smithers Junior.
Ha! Busted.
Now the movie's
turned into a play.
Still good though.
I'm sorry
I lied to you, Waylon.
But I wanted to spare you
the details of your
father's gruesome death.
Well, I'm glad to know
he died a hero
instead of that other way.
I told him his father
was killed in the Amazon
by a tribe of savage women.
I hope it didn't
affect you in any way.
We'll never know, sir.
Well, Marge, we solved
the case of
the haunted quarry.
Homer, shouldn't we
give that skull
to Mr. Smithers?
Why? He'd just bury it.
Hey! Hey! I found a clue
that's gonna bust
your mystery wide open.
Sorry.
We already solved it.
Oh.
Well, you want
to take a look at it
anyways just for ha-ha's?
Seems kind of pointless now.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
It's just that, you know,
I went to a lot of trouble,
you know,
making the envelope
and everything.
Let's see
what you have, Moe.
Okay.
Now this first thing
is just gonna look
like a used Band-Aid,
and it is.
But the rest of the stuff
don't make no sense
without it.
So, you know,
bear with me.
Wow, Moe.
You've been doing
a lot of sleuthing.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
I sleuthed my ass off
on this one.
Okay, this is a number six
from somebody's address.
Or is it a nine?
You don't know.
This is gravel.
Okay? Gravel.
This is...
That's more gravel.
Okay. Oh!
This is...
That's more gravel.
Okay. Oh!
This is a shell that, to me,
this is just me talking.
It looks like
a helmet for a mouse.
Now, that sounds crazy, right?
But if you ask
the mice about it,
they don't say nothing.
I mean,
they run the other way.
At first, I was just fishing
with the helmet thing.
But then from
the mouse reaction I got,
I got a little
more concerned.
HOMER: You really made
that envelope?
'Cause it says
"Hammermill" over here.
MOE: Um... No.
(HOMER SCREAMING)
ENGLISH - US - PSDH