Front. Nine. Eight.....
New Year is celebrated with great enthusiasm in Kartalkaya.
This New Year's Eve, as every year, more than a hundred ski instructors...
...here with the torches in their hands...
...they present an unforgettable visual feast to the enthusiastic crowd here.
We celebrate your new year. We want you to stay with love.
We wish you such a happy, loving, healthy and peaceful year, sir.
Thank you very much for being with us and watching us.
(screaming - young people having fun)
(with difficulty) No, leave it, leave it, leave it, leave it..
( celebration )
( straining ) let go, let go, let go.
( breath )
Happy New Year, Mary.
- Where? - What where?
- Where? - Stop, stop, stop.
- First, let me ask you another question? - What are you going to ask?
Are you going to kill me?
- Or are you going to have them killed? - What killing? What are you talking about?
We are not like you. I'm not like you.
You know those men, those Tevfiks, Fahris...
...we went and asked them many times.
We asked, "For God's sake, where are they?" Where?
We don't know, they said. Only Destiny knows.
Only he knows! It's been thirty years! Thirty years!
Look! I do not want anything from you!
See what you're up to! Find it from God!
But I'm begging you. Please tell me, where is it?
We hope that this new year will bring joy to our country, our world, everyone...
...brings health, tranquility, peace and happiness.
Let's not forget that every new year is a new beginning.
Yes, if we want our lives to be filled with goodness and beauty in this new year...
... let's know that this is in our hands...
If you want to make new decisions tonight, now is the time!
Yes, now let's ask our holidaymakers who are entering the new year in Kartalkaya...
Let's see what they expect from this new year.
Have they made any resolutions about what they will do in the new year?
Sir, happy new year, happy new year!
Sir, is there anything you want to say about the new year?
Where did you bury these people?
Where did you bury my father?
At least, let's find his bones! So I passed everything…
At least these people should have a grave!
I'm not the only one. Look, we are not the only ones, there are so many families.
They all want only one thing. Just finding your bones is all!
Tell those families...
...all cases have entered the statute of limitations.
What does this mean? So they will forget.
That's why... There is also a court decision...
- You have to, you will forget. - Destiny
You will do only one thing. You just tell me the location of the mass grave and that's it.
After that, whatever you do, wherever you go.
What do you want? Do you want money, how much money you want, let's meet and give it to you.
Whatever you want, I don't know, whatever you want.
There is nothing I want from you. I received what I wanted on time.
This is over. This business is closed.
He left now. It's going down.
I saw it, okay. I'm following you, don't worry.
- My wife disappeared. - When did he disappear?
It's been an hour or so. We were eating inside at the hotel. Then he got up and left...
- I keep calling but he doesn't answer. - Was there an argument or something?
No.
- You know, New Year's Eve, alcohol etc... - No, no, no, no.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
- So what? - His wife has disappeared.
How? Did he suddenly disappear, sir?
- What should I do, can you tell me? - Has this happened before?
What happened?
So, your wife went off on her own? Has he ever disappeared before?
Yes, that's what I'm saying.
How could he have "escaped"? How?
Because Fatoş is running away, father. This girl has been running away like this all her life!
Why do you think he never meets his family?
Because that guy, who will be his father, will drink and drink his mother every night...
...then he was beating Fatoş!
Is it ok? Do we have a deal now? The girl's entire childhood was like this!
Fatoş also ran away from home all the time.
He doesn't talk to anyone anyway, he never meets his mother or father.
Come on son, okay, he doesn't talk to his father, why doesn't he talk to his mother?
He is also very angry with his mother because she never left his father.
Oh, that's the kid! What does he know...
This time he escaped from me! I know.
My son, why should he run away from you?
What happened, did you do something to this girl, did you fight, what happened, what is it?
Well, I didn't do it...
What? Me? What did I do?
Ms. Zuhal...
...I'm sorry, but this is such a coincidence.
So I was reading your book, and when I saw it here, I brought it immediately.
- Can I have an autograph, please? - Of course, who should I tell?
- Filiz'e. - Filiz.
- If only I could take a selfie. - Of course.
Madam, would you excuse me?
- We are talking about something here. - Sorry, later.
You said so. Here, everything is in its place in the bedroom.
Doesn't someone who wants to escape take a few things with him?
Do you know how he got out of the house the last time he ran away, dad?
Barefoot!
My son, don't talk nonsense, for God's sake, look...
...you panicked, Deva, right now, you can't think clearly!
Is it ok. Let's say this girl ran away.
No, for example, why don't you think like this first, where are we right now...
...we are in the mountains. Snow, ice! Isn't it? Let's say this girl fell down...
...he broke his foot or leg somewhere, couldn't it be?
Why don't you think about this first?
- Then I'll go. You know those rescue teams? - Yes.
Let me go and ask them.
- Well, ask me. Ask of course. - Come on son, let me see.
Ugh, see how everything came crashing down on me?
(laugh) I'm going crazy, I'm responsible for everything.
Dad, what should we do, let's call the hospitals or something, right?
What did you say to the girl now? Of course you talked back and forth, and the girl couldn't stand it.
Is it me, everyone? (laugh)
- Did you see? - No.
Hehe, Fatoş yes.
Okay okay, thank you very much.
- My wife disappeared, have you ever seen her? - I didn't see.
- Agah! - Huh!
Is it?
(Unintelligible speeches)
Why did you return home?
I'm back.
Where were you dead?
Look, look how well I undress. (laugh) They shot your brother.
I know, mom.
They told me, come and look. Do you know me? (laugh)
I said, don't I know him, my son, he is mine.
They also laid him in such a cold place.
I said, you will freeze the boy. ( breath)
The lives of people I have never met depend on me from morning to night, right there in the air?
One jump, then you're in the void, everything is left to me.
Think about what kind of responsibility this is. Even the slightest mistake...
Oh, God forbid.
So, I treat Fatoş the same way.
As if his life depended on me too...
...I guess I'm constantly turning around like crazy...
(Nida) I drowned the girl, so!
Don't be like that, Deva, but don't blame yourself.
Wait a minute, let it happen in the morning. Let's see, of course there will be news.
Will it really come?
Of course it will come. Of course it will come.
Here you go.
They called you a murderer. Neighbors said.
I said, such a thing is not possible. He was just born, he's a baby.
How did you become a murderer, son? When did you grow up and become a murderer?
- Where are you going, stop, don't go. - I'm not going, I'm not going, I'm here.
- Oh, good. - I am her.
You go and ask your father to give you pajamas.
Oh, your brother will come soon. Oh, if you only knew how happy he will be when he sees you.
Come on, may God give you peace, my son.
İbrahim!
Is there anyone?
Where are you?
This is not here either...
Where are these guys, where are these guys?
- Agah, don't shout, you'll wake people up. - Let them wake up if they wake up!
There is no fatosh, they kidnapped the girl, who knows what they are doing.
(Don't cry)
No!
Don't be like that Agah, don't cry.
How can I not cry! They kidnapped the girl because of me, all because of me.
Who knows what they are doing now.
- Agah! Agah! - What?
I told you. I told you at the time.
I said, "Go, find these men, kill them all one by one."
But what did you say? How should I do it, Mebrure?
So what did you do next, huh?
No, let's run away to Australia with the kids, no, take me with you!
So, what happened? Did it work?
Look, they kidnapped the girl!
- Agah! - What?
Go and do your murder.
Get yourself together.
- Well, you are a repeat murderer. - Huh.
- They even called you "Dog Killer". - Huh.
Don't cry around here.
- What's that sound? Where does it come from? - For aught I know?
- Is that voice coming from you? - No, hee..
- Agah Beyoğlu. - I'm Hikmet too. Listen to me carefully...
Come on, let's get this over with. Don't let any more innocent people get hurt.
Would you like some tea?
How will we finish this?
- Come on, sit down. - I'm not sitting anywhere!
Where is Fatoş, what did you do to the girl?
Come, let's have a tea, I will tell you everything.
I wouldn't drink anything with a murderer like you!
Look, it's true. I shot a lot of people.
I have taken many lives, although not as many as you, but I did not take them from you.
What do you mean, I didn't take it, I saw it with my own eyes, you kidnapped the girl.
We missed it, I missed it. I kidnapped the girl to save her life.
What do you mean, his life should be saved?
- The girl is alive, Agah. - I don't believe you!
Where is the girl? What did you do to Fatoş? Tell the truth!
Al!
- Look at this! - What is that?
- Fatos! - Heh!
Look, he's alive!
Take a look at this!
Fatoş, are you okay, girl? Fatosh!
It's a live camera view, where should he hear it?
What, how live camera, so, is it there now?
Wow, you've completely abandoned yourself, Agah, you don't know anything about the world!
- So, is the girl alive? - Yes, he is alive.
I have a hut, it's there now right now.
So he's not dead.
- No! - God bless you.
God bless you. God bless you. I am very pleased. Ayy, thank you very much.
Hand over the girl to me.
Is that a hut or whatever it is, take me there!
That job is not that easy! Destiny doesn't know that the girl is alive.
I said it? I kidnapped him to save his life. If you just listen, you will understand me.
- Is there any sugar? - Drink without sugar. I let go, so do you.
Now Agah Effendi...
…let's say someone in your family passed away. How many days will you mourn for it?
Forty days!
Is this Destiny going to kill your family? How will he kill?
He killed someone, let's say one of us, and shot a member of your family. What will he do?
Destiny will wait forty days.
On the forty-first day, he will have another person killed. Then he will wait another forty days.
He's going to get someone killed again. Do you understand the calculation?
You will mourn for forty days!
Then you will just come out of mourning and someone else will die.
Do you know what fate told us?
We will not let that Agah Beyoğlu out of his mourning!
One mourning will end, the next will begin!
Like this, until, one by one, he killed his entire family...
...and then until I kill that dog!
This man is sick.
Well, what revenge? What have I done to whom that he is taking revenge on me?
Did you shoot your brother?
How? What about me, how should I know? Who is whose brother?
Well, you went to the prosecutor and told him!
- You said that you shot three men in Beyoğlu at night. - Yes.
Well, one of them was Kader's brother.
Them! Oh! Oh! Oh! From where to where? What does that have to do with anything?
And of course, as if you were mocking, you put a label on the children's foreheads saying "Personal".
I don't remember that! I don't remember who I shot and why?
Anyway, it's done.
Let's see how we can save your bride.
Yes, tell me that now. What are we going to do? How are we going to do?
I swear, I thought, this is the easiest way to do it.
- Lower back! Lower back! - Hi!
- Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk!
(whispering) Why does this help you?
- Wasn't this the man of Destiny? - What. Heh!
- Well, let me ask you something! - Ask.
Why are you helping me?
There was a girl. Your bride is around the same age...
That's when we got into something.
Anyway, long story short, they gave us a list.
- Who gave it? - Never mind now.
They said, these will be resolved. So we started kidnapping the men one by one and shooting them.
Anyway, one day, we went to pick up a man from this list again.
The man next to me is also excited. We even call him Crazy Jacob.
We entered the man's house. We know that some people have no one.
(Struggle sounds)
It turns out that he has a daughter at university in Istanbul. At that time, school was on holiday and the girl came out.
We've captured the man and are taking him away.
( Scream )
Of course it was a mess. At that moment, the man untied his hands and jumped on us...
- (Struggling sounds) - Stop!
- Stop! - Let me go, let me go.
( breath )
Of course, we couldn't leave the girl there.
I said, "- I have a hut, let's lock it there for now."
( Scream )
(Scream-Crying)
What should we do? Should we call Kader?
We made a phone call to Kader somewhere. I spoke.
What did he say?
There is such a situation that...
...if I said to Yakup, Destiny said, leave the girl alone, scare her and leave her.
Neither Kader nor Yakup will know that I am lying.
Such a task.
But me, at that moment! Whatever mood I'm in.
How I became a tin soldier like this. I couldn't tell that lie.
Actually, I wanted to say.
I said, tell me what will happen! Tell a lie and the girl's life will be saved.
I couldn't do it. So there is. No one would know about it.
But it didn't happen.
That evening...
Destiny is not there, I acted as Destiny to myself. Do you understand?
"Shoot the girl," he said.
ok
I couldn't sleep at all after that.
That's why... When it comes to fate, Agah's family will die first.
It never occurred to me from the beginning.
I said, this only happens once. I will never shoot anyone who is not in a fight again.
Then he said, go and kidnap someone. I volunteered too.
He gave Crazy Yakup to me again, as if there was no other man.
History will repeat itself, but I'm not the same!
We picked up your bride from the hotel. We took it.
You wait, I'll handle it.
- Quiet, quiet. Come here slow. Heh. - (Exclamation-crying)
- Come, walk. Calm down. - (Exclamation-crying)
Thank God for Yakup's life, he also has fifty problems.
No, his back hurts, no, he has hemorrhoids...
- Don't make noise, don't make noise. - (crying) Let go! Leave!
(cry)
Shsht.
So, you see, Jacob also knows that his daughter is dead.
Now, if I hand over this bride to you...
...Kader will definitely know about it.
Then he sends someone else and has him shoot him.
As I told you, it will make you mourn for forty days.
This means he will wait forty days until he kills someone else.
What I say to you is this:
Let me keep this girl so she can survive!
Let me tell you, that's all we have, we just killed the girl.
But don't expect more.
Whatever problem you have with Agah, go and solve it with Agah.
Don't involve his family or anything.
Is useful? I don't know.
But is it worth a try? Well worth it.
Because... that evening I...
...that I couldn't come out of that phone booth and lie...
I am so sorry.
Ha, let's say it didn't work.
At least your bride will be saved. Ready Destiny also knows he is dead.
How will all this end now? Of course it will end because one day...
...then I will release the girl and she will go away.
But let me tell you something. Do you regret it now? Because the girl died.
It's not just that, Hikmet.
You know, they gave you a list and you killed them all.
What will their burden be?
In other words, that burden cannot be lightened by saving just one life!
Are you going to get away with this just because you saved Fatoş's life?
Your sentence is seventeen life imprisonments!
I wish I said that.
You didn't say! Can I say, are you a child?
The man is doing something on his own there to save the girl.
Am I going to confuse the man by saying these things now?
Then his conscience is his own conscience, it is his own business, his own problem.
The girl is safe, that's important.
- You did wrong, but I think. - Why?
You were going to put the gun to her head, you were going to find out where the girl was!
You would find the girl, you would kill this Hikmet.
Then you were going to kill the others.
Oh, so you're saying, go shoot them all.
You can kill people, I swear, Mebrure!
Well, I don't need to do anything.
I'll just sit and wait for news from Hikmet, that's all.
Oh, and of course I have to move the kids somewhere else.
Because they know the address of the hotel.
Destiny won't attack right away, that's obvious... I still need moisture.
Wow! There is a cure, a cure! The kid is going crazy...
Who knows how curious he is about Fatoş?
Won't you say anything to him?
- Wouldn't I say? - Well, then, whatever you say.
( Laugh )
My cure, I swear I was abandoned too at the time,
Stuff like this happened to me when I was young.
You won't mind, son, you won't mind, one goes, the other comes.
Especially a handsome man like you, I swear they won't let you go!
So grandpa, what you say is so useless right now.
So it doesn't work that well.
Besides, she's my wife! Fatosh is my wife.
How can I not worry!
No, it's not comfortable for me at all.
Oh my son, trust me. I feel such things, I swear, look.
Fatoş is fine, she has nothing.
As you said, it goes like that from time to time.
Apparently the girl is listening to her head.
You too, don't bother. So don't do too much, girl. What?
Where are we going, at least tell me.
- Aren't you a paratrooper? - I am, huh?
Well, you must know how to jump into unfamiliar places.
Come on, jump, come on, come on, step on the gas, come on, come on. (laugh)
I'll take this, I'll take that, I'll take that too.
- Dear Deva, what do you want? - I don't want anything, thank you.
- Son, tell me something and I'll buy it for you too. - I don't want it, grandpa.
My son, you need to eat, you will still grow.
A child in his developmental age needs to eat, right?
- Oh grandpa! - What!
How do you do this!
- Huh? - What am I doing?
No fatosh, grandpa! My wife is nowhere to be seen!
But you're just kidding like nothing happened!
I haven't blinked an eye since the night thinking that this phone was going to ring!
(message sound)
- Oh, he came. - What came?
I swear, a message came from Fatoş!
From Fatoş?
( Horn sound )
Did the message come from Fatoş? Are you sure?
Yeah yeah. I'm calling but he still doesn't answer.
What does he write, what does he say?
Destiny separated us...
- Destiny? - Yes, that's what he wrote.
Destiny separated us. But fate will bring us together again, he says.
And he says hello.
- To who? - To you!
Come on Fatoş, please pick up the phone. Come on my Fatoş!
As I said, there is not a single Agah in me.
But there are lots of them.
In fact, they are all angry with each other.
No, actually I said it wrong. I should have said sad, not angry.
Instead of a lot, a bouquet...
...yes...I have a bouquet of Agah inside me.
Because when I see what this world is like,
...such a sadness fell on me... I was crushed under it like a flower.
That's why I have neither scent nor color left in this deep blue world.
I am not between two pages of a notebook...
...I am a dried flower among millions of people.