( breath )
Oh dad, what a big deal you are!
You really didn't sit on your butt, it sank easily.
You lifted us all up. Ugh!
We haven't even had breakfast yet.
We'll do it girl, we'll do it, we'll do it when we get to the hotel.
No, also, for example, when did you book this hotel?
I set it up for a while.
- So we couldn't say goodbye to Mr. Tevfik. - Heh, I saw him.
I told you we were going. He said hello.
There is no father, you are stubborn! So you said what you said, it doesn't work like that.
You nailed it, you woke us all up early in the morning!
Of course I will remove it. This is my dream, baby.
- I've dreamed of this all my life. - What?
( Laugh )
(Unintelligible speeches)
- Wow, wow, wow, wow. - Here you go.
- Here you go, welcome. - Oh!
- (laughing) Dad, what did you do? - It will happen only once every forty years. Wow!
Dad, where did you find all this money?
- There was Mr. Tevfik. - Yes.
After you went to bed, we played poker with him until the morning.
(Breath) Dad, I swear, you are feared!
- It's obvious you ruined the man. - Aah, but I didn't do anything.
- You definitely ruined the man. (laughing) - He scratched his own itch.
(Fun shouts)
- Come here. Oops! - Dear Dad.
Were you able to ask about this Agah Beyoğlu? Did you find out why he was after you?
I couldn't ask anything, Meryem. I couldn't even speak properly.
You're right, of course. When you suddenly appear in front of you...
But I think there is! Agah is also their man.
No matter how they hid the name of the man, we haven't even heard of him all these years and all the research.
You just leave him alone. So what do we do now?
What will I say to this Destiny?
Give me my name. Let's come and meet as soon as possible.
- Are you sure? - Haven't we been waiting for this for years, Ruhi?
A lifetime has passed after these guys.
Have you reviewed this? What?
- No, I didn't examine it. - Look!
We are looking for Agah Beyoğlu. He was staying here with his family…
Just a second, sir, I'm checking right away.
(Unintelligible speeches)
- Sir, they checked out this morning. - Where did they go? Does anyone know?
So we cannot provide information about our guests. Please excuse me.
(Unintelligible speeches)
- Well, I call a nightlife friend and ask immediately. - Well, let's call.
Hello Farouk. Now there is a gentleman here…
- No, I don't know who he is. - Safety.
He was from the police.
So right now, I can already see him showing his ID.
So he wants information about our guests.
Spiritual! I gave you two days' grace period.
Why did you rush, brother?
So, tell me, who is so curious about our title?
Well, he wasn't a stranger...
Let him move on, I'll find him. Come on.
They are here.
Now we will do it like this. He gathered this Agah dynasty here.
We will have to distribute it.
We will take it one by one, Hikmet. Whichever one falls into our hands...
Here you go.
(Breath) How's it going? Are you bored of us?
- ( Laughing ) I'm not bored. -Huh.
They are all sweet people actually.
- That's fine. - Especially your grandfather.
Huh, it's very sweet.
( breath )
Did you bored?
Well...
- Of course, I might be a little bored. -Are you a little bored?
- I mean, I don't know, a little bit, I guess. - Really?
You're going to get it, is it a problem, huh, Fatoş?
- Are you going to take it or is it a problem, Fatoş? Huh? - I don't know.
(Unintelligible speeches)
So what's wrong with this? Talk to me, huh? Agah! Agah! Don't be silent, speak.
Well, he has been your son-in-law for how many years, he is now considered your son.
Don't be shy, go and talk. Agah! Agah!
Come on, come on. Come on, come on, come on. Run.
Dear Ertan!
- Oh, daddy, come, come, sit, sit. - Sit down
(Breath) Do you know? Actually, I understood that day.
- What did you get? - You know, I asked you, who didn't want me?
- I don't understand? - Didn't you take me and look after me at home?
You left it at the nursing home.
Then I said, who didn't want me? Of course, you couldn't answer correctly either.
But I understood. It was Zuhal, wasn't it?
- No, daddy. - No no. Now...
I have a request from you.
I say, you should talk to Zuhal.
If you take me with you. Let's all go to Australia together. Huh?
What do you say? I just sit in a corner and I won't be a burden to you.
So tell us as soon as possible so that we can make preparations, here is the passport, visa, fee stamp...
...Anyway, let's handle them, huh? What do you say?
Oh, daddy, I'll talk and talk...
...you were going to talk, I mean, you were going to say okay, I got better, my memory came back.
- We were going to leave, you were going to stay. - Well, okay, I talked...
...I spoke. I said, girl, I remember, I remember everything.
He didn't believe that he was awake!
Well, that's why you should talk to him as soon as possible.
She already wants to go to Australia, but she's afraid to stay here.
- Why should he be afraid, father! - Well, he pulled a gun.
Oh daddy, that issue is over. Years have passed and the man is no longer there.
- Who's missing? - Dog Killer.
- Serial killer. - Huh!
My son! What you said is not Turkish.
There is no such thing as serial killer in Turkish.
- So what do we say? - Also a repeat murderer.
Well, whatever it is, it's done. He killed twenty people.
- Why? - Well, it's not clear.
Look at the internet, you look at it for everything! It's written there.
No, daddy, he didn't write anything. So it's not clear. What's done is done, it's over.
You know, my father is mentally ill. She's wearing a cat costume!
Whatever he thinks he is now. He's just a poor guy. It's crazy, dad.
Do you know how a person feels when he finds out he is a repeat murderer?
He doesn't feel anything. But I guess a man who feels doesn't become a repeat murderer.
He says, "I wonder what reason I had for committing all those murders?"
So okay, after all, I'm just a grumpy guy who gets excited about everything.
But people cannot be killed in this!
I wonder what happened, Agah, who was an ant-crusher of forty years, left and became the Dog Killer!
Poor Agah, he took the gun in his hand, how old is the man disguised as a cat...
...why did you hide in that costume?
If only I could remember! I will finally understand who I am.
Dog Killer or Agah Beyoğlu?
Tewfik! Don't tire yourself out. It'll be fine, it'll be fine.
Everything will pass.
(difficulty breathing)
Tevfik, you released three men from the list.
(breath) In this case, you deserve to die three times.
(choking sounds)
(Unintelligible speeches)
Baba!
You don't hear it either, no one hears it!
( scream )
Baba!
(Unintelligible speeches)
Fatosh, you tell me, my secretive son, he never tells such things.
Tell me what happens, I'm very curious, how did you meet, what happened with Deva?
- One day I watch a video. - What.
There, they show people jumping with parachutes.
- (laugh) - I said okay, I'll do it too.
- I went to Ölüdeniz. - What.
I packed everything and left the house. But how afraid I am.
- What. - I mean, my legs are shaking up there.
I was going to jump there with a teacher, I said sorry, I can't do it.
At that time, a man next to me said, Deva!
It calmed me down so well.
He said to me, I will make you fly.
We flew. We're still flying.
Do you know where this Deva's supreme calming ability comes from?
From me! I mean, when I say "from me", it doesn't mean "it was attracted to me", I mean...
My baby, he tried so hard with me...
- Oh... You know, right? - I know, you're an alcoholic.
(Exhale)
- Zuzu, I have something to tell you. - What.
I am very afraid of alcoholics.
And not just from alcoholics. That can be addicted to anything...
...I'm actually more afraid of everyone than anyone else.
Do you know how it feels to me?
It's like you can do anything at any time.
...as if a wild animal was standing in front of me and could attack me at any moment...
Or as if he would suddenly leave me and leave me at the moment when I trusted him the most.
That's why Zuzu...
- I expect everything from you. - I understand very well what you mean.
But let me make you a promise.
I will neither attack you nor abandon you.
Do you know when I'm most afraid of alcoholics?
When they promised me.
So Zuzu, you better not make any promises to me. You give me time. Is it possible?
This is a very strange girl, huh. I told you...
...when we came here five years ago....
...he brought a girl again, he found a girl named Süveda...
...the girl doesn't talk at all, then this girl shot a boy, one of her ordinary friends.
You know, pretty much like that, he shot him with a gun.
That's why I'm asking, is there really something in Devada?
(whisper) Where is the moon, there is a maniac. This kid finds it, I wonder why?
Dear Ertan, look, I do not accept this.
Ha, me, I became addicted because of my father.
But Deva did not become like this because of her mother.
( Breath ) So this happened because of me.
If there is a madman or a maniac, he finds them.
The child imitates his father. Isn't it?
- (sigh) - Oh okay, I'm kidding.
- You're not doing it, Ertan. - I'm just kidding.
- You don't. Let there be love. - Allah! Allah!
I thought a lot that day. Then I said, Agah, don't mess with it, leave the past behind.
Whatever happened happened, everything is clear.
Since you were able to commit murder over and over again. You're obviously used to horror.
In fact, you've gotten so used to it that you're worse than mad.
But it's over now. Maybe I can't change the past, but...
...I decide what will happen next, and most importantly, who I will be.
And that evening, right there, I resigned from my past.
I said yes, maybe I was a repeat murderer once, but...
...I will not repeat myself anymore.
- What happened, are you upset about something? - No.
There is something here.
I have a son, who should I tell about it?
- Tell me. - What.
- I always told you everything I had to say. - My problem is with myself.
What will happen if I tell you? What will happen if I don't tell you?
Grandpa, what do you say? Look how well you are healing.
- Huh. - I'm following too.
- You're getting better every day. - Really.
- Of course. - Huh.
Am I a good person?
Look, I won't know about that now.
It also depends on what's happening here.
Do you remember this? What? You know, you were always doing this to me.
No, I didn't remember. But I better not remember...
...I remember too much already.
- I'm glad you remembered, grandfather, I'm glad you remembered. - Hey my lion. ( laugh)
Oohh! Grandfather and grandson, no one hugs us
- Come, come, come, let's hug. (laugh) - I'm coming.
Come on of course..
- Oh... my dear daughter. - How am I?
You look so stylish, I make you look like a singer...
- What was his name? - Heh!. Am I cool?
- I understand. - Heh. Yes yes, do you understand?
(cheerful laughter)
(My beautiful sons, their mother's lambs, may God not separate us)
(Unintelligible speeches)
(new year celebration)
(cheerful new year's conversation)
(Unintelligible speeches)
(sellers-children-amusement park)
(screaming sounds)
( Scream - joyful sounds )
(rising screams)
( kids - clown - fun )
Thank you sister-in-law, thank you. Let's have a happy new year.
- Happy new year Yakup, say hello to your sisters. - Aleykumselam.
Wisdom! For God's sake, what is he doing in the middle of the night?
It's no big deal.
- I'll take care of it and come back in the morning. Don't worry. - Allah! Allah!
- Come on, happy new year. - Happy new year.
(Hard breathing)
(Street entertainment sounds)
(breathing sound)
(Unintelligible speeches)
- Dad! - What.
Look, everyone always has tattoos around here.
- Should we get a tattoo for you too? - Wow, what a tattoo, for God's sake, Zuhal.
No, but let me explain, let me tell you an idea.
Do you know what we will do?
I think it would be great to have AGAH written like this with a letter on each finger.
- It would be very nice, too. - ( laugh)
- Would you like another glass? - I do not drink.
In the past, tattoos were only available to sailors.
It actually happens to prisoners.
- Well, that's why everyone has tattoos now. - Of course.
So everyone feels like they are in prison.
Yes, we heard that there is a great Tango master among us.
- Dad! - What.
We invite him to the track to spice up our New Year's Eve.
- Either leave it or not now. Leave it to Zuhal, please. No. - Please, Dad, please.
- Tell your mother something. - Oh, say something too.
- Ahh! - Come on dad, please, please come on.
And voila. Tango champion, Agah Beyoğlu is coming.
(laugh) girl..
Oh, it's so sweet.
(applause-cheering)
- Thanks. - Oh! Thank you very much.
Dad, have you seen you, you are gorgeous, just like before. You never forgot.
(continue applause)
- Yes. - Mr. Agah, I see that you have not lost any of your form.
Oh sir. We did something.
- Well, I'm coming...right away. - Like meditation...
...or this year, we definitely have to go to Australia, girl, I'm sure you'll love it.
I'm going to the toilet, my love. See you later.
See you soon, darling.
Let me go to this room and change my clothes.
- I'm not used to this, you know. - Oh, my dear Deva!
If you're going to go to the room, bring my father's medicine. Your mother forgot.
- Daddy, will you drink your medicines? - We have to drink.
Okay, okay, let me go and get it.
(whispering) Ertan, Ertan, come on.
What happened, are we going to Australia? Have you talked to Zuhal?
Oh, I haven't been able to talk yet, I haven't had the chance, dad, I will.
Son, what did I tell you? Didn't I say we should leave as soon as possible? Allah! Allah!
- What's going on? - He becomes blind.
My son! Why can't you talk to your wife? Why can't you say anything?
Okay, I'll tell you, I'll talk, okay.
Okay, I will say, I will talk, I will, I will...
...your life was like this. Such is your life. I couldn't understand you, I really couldn't understand you.
I never understood. You are wandering around...
...it is not clear what you are doing, it is not clear whether you are present or not.
Tell me, what is your purpose in this life?
- What use are you? - Me?
I act as a figuration in the story of the Beyoğlu family.
I'll go out and get some fresh air.
( Laugh )
Sir dear, are you going to say something?
- I was going to say don't upset Deva again. - What?
Whatever you're doing right now, don't let it be anything that will upset Deva.
- As you said, he tried hard with me at the time. - Yes.
And don't bother with that.
Aah! Had size bucket.
(Fun sounds)
(Enthusiasm - cheering)
(Enthusiasm - cheering continues below)
- Is it clear who we will take? - No, whatever comes along.
( Laugh )
(Unintelligible speeches)
Remedy! Ah! Let me go, let me go, let me go aahh, aah, let me go, let me go, let me go.
Sometimes one feels so alone or so helpless...
...he says okay, I understand. This world is a trap set against me...
...even a mine. I stepped on it the day I was born.
If I move my foot now, that big world will blow up.
That's why you freeze where you stand. He's afraid to even breathe.
All that remains is loneliness. And an enemy.