Once upon a time, I was afraid that I would forget everything.
What I experienced, what I did,
...I was devastated with fear that I would forget what kind of person I was.
But now I remember it all.
What I experienced, what I did,
...what kind of person was I? I know it all now.
The strange thing is…
I'm even more afraid now.
Oh, my body hurts everywhere.
Good morning!
Oh, Ertan, what happened to us? We went to sleep so early last night that we stayed up.
Well, it's good, my dear.
Me too, I'm tired of running here and there,
...we got some rest, okay?
I'm a bit dizzy too.
It's like this, I took sleeping pills and lots of them...
Now get up, wash your hands and face, and I'll prepare breakfast.
Okay, let me take care of my father's medicine first, then.
No, don't worry, your father is not at home.
How come?
The man has been saying since yesterday that he should go for a walk or something.
He probably went for a walk.
Well, I guess Ertan, a human being...
...won't he call and ask, for God's sake!
Oh, this is Kambura my love, it's a tiny place!
It's a place your father knows, so what will happen!
Where is this phone of mine? Where is this phone of mine? Heh!
- Oh my God, Ertan. -Okay okay.
Look, there is no Deva either.
Apparently he also went to Fatoş.
- Oh, let it go. - So this issue has also been resolved.
So okay, you can relax, everything is taken care of. Is it ok?
- Oh, where did I put it? - Something to wonder about, my dear!
Well, let's take care of each other a little. We were left alone.
At the end of forty years.
Deva!
- Destiny! - Don't shout, don't shout,
- ...I will take you to Destiny. - Where is Deva?
- You didn't do anything to my grandchild, did you? - Good good…
- You'll see for yourself now. - Well, okay, where is it, let's go.
- Wait a minute, wait. - Stop what?
- Let's see, are you full or empty? - Oh, I'm full, of course I'm full.
I'm full, can't I be full, I'm full to the brim, I'm fed up.
- Raise your arms up. - Yes, that's what you're saying, no, I'll get moody.
- Oh, wait! - I get moody.
- Lift, lift. - Your temper....
Aaa!
What more could there be!
What do I do? You kidnapped my grandchild!
Should I come with a broken-ass gun? I swear, if I found it, I would come with a tank.
Oh, I always wanted to have one of these, too.
Wow, that was great, heh!
My luck is today.
- Is there anything else? - Nothing else, anything else.
Ya, al, al, al hadi al, al! Al, bunu da al... Al!
Another?
Nothing.
Al, al hadi, bir de bu var al!
Take it, take it, you carry it anyway, like a dead donkey, they all take it, you carry it.
Do you know who painted this picture?
I don't know, how should I know?
Damn, it would happen to me that...
…I was going to cut off your ears!
They destroyed my dear wall! Look at this! Like the devil!
Is this really you, heh? Destiny says so.
No, you are in no mood to be evil!
Of course not, what did you think!
Go, go, go.
-Oh, I want to talk to you about something, Zuhal. - Huh!
Opening! Don't open, don't open!
Opening.
Oh, maybe it's my father.
Heh, he's here.
Who is calling?
There's Sajan, he's calling.
I'm tired of this guy!
He gave us a drug and took over our lives, man!
Is there a call in the morning and evening, does such a thing happen?
Saturn! Opening.
Opening.
Zuhal, hang up that phone.
Quarter
What are you doing!
What are you doing, are you crazy, why are you screaming?
Is there something between you and this guy?
Whatever you say, it doesn't matter.
Then why is this guy trying like a maniac with you?
I told you this, Ertan.
This man read my book and was very impressed.
"You saved my life," this man says to me. What more can you say?
That's why he helps us.
Your book doesn't save lives, my dear.
Those ridiculous "get back to life" talk,
...doesn't do shit in real life! Let him know.
Don't fool yourself!
You wrote something, and I embellished it...
...I packaged it and sold it. That's it.
You say these just to upset me!
No, I'm telling the truth!
Especially if you cheated on me with this guy...
With this guy too?
I remember, I remember everything.
Who did I kill, why did I kill...
...every time I killed, I remember them all.
Leave Deva, do whatever you want to do to me.
So now you remember everything.
Tell me!
Why did you kill my brother?
One evening, we were out with a lady friend...
- Shut up! Go ahead. - Who are they, Agah?
-What are you doing, isn't it shameful? - Get out, uncle.
- Come on uncle, come out. - Agah
- Come on uncle, come on uncle. Come on! - What the hell is going on?
Aaa!.. A****** the damn clown..
You now...
...did you kill my brother for this?
Because they were rude to you.
So, did our boy pull a gun on you?
- No! - Heh!
So there is no self-defense.
Just because they pushed you around a lady.
You couldn't resist! You said, "Can this be done to me?"
...you pulled the gun and shot them all.
Well, won't you give up, Ertan?
Aren't you tired? How many years passed? When will this end?
Ok. I cheated.
When I came here, I met a man, and after that...
Don't tell, I don't want to tell, don't tell!
Okay, so why, constantly, endlessly...
...are you implying this to me?
Ertan, if you couldn't forget me, why didn't you leave me?
I know why. You want me to be indebted to you.
Look at me while drinking! Hop! A debt immediately.
Then I came here, I made a mistake, okay.
You did great, thank you. Oh, there's a debt there too.
You have never forgiven me, Ertan.
You always calculated debt, debt.
Look, I swear to you, Ertan, you are a loan shark.
What you are doing is called emotional usury!
Beautiful.
You came up with a very nice saying,
...you can write about this in your other book too!
No, it's just like that.
Whatever you gave, you are now getting back with interest!
- Do you know what I was going to tell you just now? - Oh, what were you going to say, Ertan?
I was going to say let's take your father to Australia.
Let him live with us, let him stay with us,
...I was going to say let's be together.
God! God!
You didn't want it at all?
You know, even if you died, you wouldn't live in the same house with Agah Beyoğlu, you Ertan!
Yes, I still think so, I still say so.
- Huh! - But just for you,
...I just thought it would be like that for you.
Oh! So you were going to write me another debt, right Ertan?
Heh! You were going to write me another debt.
You actually owe me.
You owe me money, why should I tell you?
Because you have failed every job you have ever undertaken.
Then you see, aah!
Zuhal does something that makes money like this.
...that's why you didn't leave me.
You stayed with me for money, Ertan!
You stayed for the money!
Are others like that too?
Kim?
Did they also misbehave with you? Is that why you shot all those men?
There is a district called Kambura.
Years ago,
...fifty men there, (breath)
…raped a little girl.
And none of them were prosecuted.
So I went after these.
I killed what I caught.
Wow Wow wow.
So you have dispensed justice.
(Nida) I did what was necessary.
Jacob!
We knew this guy, the leading maniac,
Turns out he was a hero!
Agah Effendi, are you a hero?
- No I'm not! - What are you then?
I don't know!
Agah sir look!
Either you use this weapon, or this weapon uses you.
You have become a prisoner of this weapon!
You thought killing was a game!
Inside it is my brother, struggling on the ground,
...you burst out laughing. You laugh.
There is this place. This place does not forget!
He knows exactly what the hell he's doing.
I'm sorry, Destiny.
Don't apologize to me.
Apologize to Deva.
(breath)
Saturn!
I am going.
To where?
I think it's over now.
Let's not hurt or upset each other anymore.
I want to leave.
Hah, here we go again! Which one is this?
No, I'm very serious this time.
Ah, you were very serious then too. You told me you want to leave,
...then we got up and came here and we were miserable with Deva.
Just wait, you too!
Ertan!
This time, I want to leave.
Is it ok? This time, I want to leave; Because...
...because you said this many times and couldn't manage it...
Let me handle this this time!
I mean, let's go, everyone, go ahead!
Well, all right!
Then you talk to Deva.
Why am I talking? You talk to Deva.
Call your son,
...say son, like this, we are leaving with your mother.
But be sure to tell us why we broke up. He asks because he is a child.
You know, you were taking care of everything.
You will talk to Deva.
You will talk to Deva, Ertan.
Because you've been running away from everything your whole life.
This time you will talk to Deva.
Call the child and tell him.
Deva da zaten...
...he has more trouble than he can handle, my child.
He is just trying to make amends with Fatoş.
And he will feel sorry for us!
Ertan!
You're not going anywhere without talking to Deva.
(breath-exclamation)
Remedy! Cure my son! Deva, let go, I'll take you out.
Destiny! Destiny, let the child go.
- Let the child go, you... - Shh... Wait a minute!
...then do whatever you want with me. Leave!
- Master Agah! - What?
That job is not that easy.
Since you are healed, you remember everything. It will be worse.
- Well, Hikmet told you! - What? What did he say?
Well, he told you.
Just because fate won't take you out of mourning.
Oh, Destiny, don't do it, Destiny.
Do you understand now? What kind of a trap are you in?
But this upset us at Hikmet.
He said he would handle it, but he couldn't.
Turns out he cheated us.
Of course, when I learned this...
...I wondered who I should take out the pain of this stake on.
From you!
Destiny, don't do it, let me love your eyes, don't do it, okay.
I'm sorry, I made a mistake. I am sorry.
- Oh, shut up. - I'm sorry, let the child go.
Your problem is with me. Will you kill me then, what will he do?
... do whatever you want, just leave the child.
Deva!
My son!
Now I'm going to ask you a question, see if you can figure it out.
Destiny, Destiny, let the child go.
- How do you get a snake out of its hole? - Stop, stop, Destiny.
Don't do it, fate! Destiny!
Don't make it fate,
- ...let me love your eyes, don't do it, don't do it. - You'll say it sweetly, right? Huh?
- Hey! But wrong. - Let the child go.
Do you know what the truth is?
To pull a snake out of its hole,
- ...you will kill your wife first. - Huh! Huh!
Here you are too
- ...you came out of your hole and came here. - Don't do it, Destiny! Destiny!
Don't do it, fate!
- Don't let me care for your eyes, let the child go. - Wait man, stop!
Let the child go.
Your brother Hikmet could not handle this.
Don't act like fate!
But I do this
- ...I stabbed his wife in the throat. - Huh! Huh!
(breath-exclamation)
Ahh!
Ahhh!
Deva! Deva!
Remedy! Remedy! My son. Deva, my son. Remedy.
Remedy! Remedy! Deva open your eyes.
Open your eyes, forgive me, forgive me, forgive me, forgive me, forgive me.
Deva! Deva!
Wake up my son, wake up my child, wake up my grandfather,
...wake up my dear, wake up my son, wake up.
Remedy! Remedy! Help! Help!
Deva! Deva! Deva!
My son!
Is there anyone? Remedy!
Mr. Agah! Here, sign this.
It's called Dog Killer.
Farm...
Donkeys...
Jacob...
Interesting…
Kader?
The famous Destiny is also involved, huh?
God! God!
Do you remember me?
I said, "You have Alzheimer's?" and he forgot me.
I did not forget.
You didn't forget but…
You have seen dreams again, Mr. Agah.
The man you call destiny is already dead and gone.
He neither dies nor dies, he is simply alive.
He made us all miserable, he did everything.
You got it mixed up, Mr. Agah!
Dog Killer shot both your grandson and his wife.
You forgot to mention that.
Yakup shot Deva.
Destiny also killed Fatoş! He confessed it himself!
This guy is taking revenge.
I told you that I killed so many people,
...you didn't believe me,
... I killed his brother,
- ...that's why he's after my family. - Wait a minute, wait a minute…
Are you the one who killed the dog? Are you telling me that?
No, then, we'll let you in right away.
Go in and go to jail. You will die inside.
But you say Destiny is alive,
On top of that, he wants to take revenge on you.
Well, to your daughter and son-in-law,
...what will happen next, I don't know.
You are also one of them.
You also work with Kader!
Look! It's all because of Alzheimer's.
I told you. Destiny is dead and gone.
Just tell me this.
Are you the Dog Killer?
Think carefully, Mr. Agah, think carefully and answer accordingly.
I can't believe it! I cant believe.
What does this want from us? No, what have we done to this?
My dear Zuhal! Come sit down my dear. Sit down for a while.
Oh, Ertan, look, this Dog Killer...
What did the despicable creature called ... want from my son?
First, first he pulled a gun on me,
...father was not enough, now he wants to kill my son.
No, what did we do to this woman called Nevra?
...what does he want from us, what is his problem with us?
He shot at me too, I wish he had shot me,
- I wish he had shot me. - Dad, I'm so sorry.
...I'm sorry, I got into Deva's trouble,
...I forgot you, who knows how scared you were!
I was scared, I was scared yes.
(breath)
Now there is something I don't understand, dad.
So Deva wasn't going to meet Fatoş?
- Yes! - Let me call him!
Also, this girl's phone is always off.
It was as if the ground opened up and this girl entered it.
It was so. Unfortunately, that's what happened.
You were telling something, dad, tell me.
- What? - You were telling something.
Well, now...
Deva!
It woke me up in the morning.
- Dad! - He said take me to Istanbul, heh?
- Didn't you say that he left the evening? - No.
Oh my God! Allah! I remember like,
...as if we were sleeping, you came...
...you woke me up like this, you asked me where Deva is,
- True, true, true. - Did I dream?
No no. You, you remember correctly.
Me too, I thought so too, I thought it was in Istanbul too.
It turns out that the boy didn't go, he went for a walk.
Morning came.
He took me, anyway, I took this, we were on the road, I was stuck.
I said let me do it here, somewhere to the side, I stopped.
It turns out that Deva also got out of the car.
I saw this Dog Killer coming towards us, shooting.
He shot the child.
So, dad, did he leave you like that, did he just leave?
Oh, there was a car, he jumped in the car and left.
Oh, I can't understand this, dad, this woman, this person, this one,
...how did he find you on the intercity road, how did he manage to do this?
- Weren't you with him? - He, he, he, the police, the police told me about that.
The police here at the hospital told me.
He said to you, they put a tracking device.
I said, what is that?
He said, look, he took out something like this, as if he had put it with his hand,
...such a black box.
I said, what is this?
From the military or what? What military said?
...they sell it for three cents at the electricians' bazaar.
Something like that.
So where is this tool?
- Where should I look, where is the tool? - Heh, heh? They took it, they took the tool.
- Who took? - The police took it.
Well, I guess it will burn something that will be fingerprinted, I don't know.
Aah!
Is there any progress?
Calm, calm, please.
- We did everything we could. - Yes.
He lost a lot of blood.
For now, all values ​​are stable.
Oh, thank God!
- But unfortunately he is in a coma. - Huh!
Of course, it is not possible to say how long this situation will last.
But don't worry, we do it with all our means,
...we will do everything we can.
- Ah! My aunt came. - What?
How did he know?
Apparently this Dog Killer is after us, girl.
We can't go home anymore. He knows the exact address.
We will stay at your aunt's. This is the best.
But you always fight, dad?
You leave me now, how is Deva?
(nida)
Deva!
He's sleeping, my beautiful son.
You know, they say he's in a coma, but...
It looks like he's sleeping to me.
Oh, my baby. Oh my dear.
It'll be okay, Deva. It will be good…
- Hopefully! Hopefully! - Hopefully!
I'm so angry with you!
- Why? - Why didn't you call me earlier?
Why don't you say you came to your senses and got better?
Come on, these are kids!
- At least call! - Well, I called, there you go.
Hey, my aunt,
...now my father told you that we would come and stay with you, but...
...we won't disturb you at all.
So don't be ridiculous! I wish I hadn't heard of it!
Agah told me everything.
(laugh) So let's ask, is it a cat or a dog?
...Is he a murderer, whatever the hell he is, come and see what I do to him.
(prayer is recited)
Everyone is gone.
- Was the funeral crowded? - I brought you halva, take it.
It was crowded.
But most of them came for gossip.
Why did he commit suicide, how did he commit suicide?
They always whispered about this. Just lie down for a while.
Oh, Melek, I'm sorry too, it came at such a wrong time.
Don't be ridiculous, of course you will come.
Was that half-witted Yakup going to take care of you?
- Heh, lie down. - Ahh, wait slow, ahh.
Ay, ay, should I put another pillow behind you?
Oh, no, no, thank you.
I knew it would be like this.
I knew one day he would do something to himself.
You know, now you're saying it.
You know, how did this wound happen, Melek, you say don't ask?
It was the same with Hikmet.
Without saying anything,
...he left without saying anything to anyone.
Ah! Ah!
What did you do, Yunus?
What did you do, how many years have passed,
Hikmet could never forget,
He went as far as taking his own life.
So, what did you do to make this happen?
Who did you hurt that made this situation come to this?
Whose curse did you take?
(breath) Come on.
Eat halvan.
(unintelligible speech)
(breath)
You know, all the cases should be gathered together,
...we were trying to file a lawsuit again for a while.
- What! what!
Thank you, the prosecutor at that time was very interested in our file.
Even...
...I went to everyone, but no one listened...
...only you accepted it. Thank you again for that.
What do you mean, our duty!
"I looked, I have a lot of documents, documents," he says.
He's obviously done a lot of research.
I said, bring it now, immediately!
I thought I'd check it out immediately.
What did he find? Is there any new information or finding?
Do you have something in your hand that we don't have?
I know, thank you.
Uh...
That's why we disturbed you.
Who's this?
Kader.
What are you saying?
Well, we know this man is dead?
Is his hometown known?
We don't know, but it's here, in Istanbul.
We even have a friend, Ulaş. He was following Destiny.
Then?
As far as we know, Destiny met this person.
His name is Yakup Sevindir. From Kader's team.
Then Ulaş disappeared.
Mary! Why didn't you let me know sooner?
Why are you trying to handle these things alone!
We are here!
Well, I will say the same thing again. I'm glad you came to me!
If it were anyone else, they wouldn't believe that these were Fate.
But I believe in you!
From where?
Because we are in this cause together!
In that case...
- We have an opening in two days. - What!
We are opening the monument to the missing 17s.
We are waiting for you too.
Besides, you give a speech. What would be nice.
Dear Mr. Fariz, I would love to…
...now if we appear there as prosecutors...
...we can't solve these issues here.
But you open it,
...I promise that I will come and visit you in a quiet time.
Definitely.
(cry)
That young Fatoş is dead and gone...
Deva is dying in a hospital room.
But this treacherous world continues to spin as if nothing happened.
I said, "If that's the case, I'll be back."
I will return to the past when I resigned.
I will become a murderer again.
That's why I went to that lawyer.
So that he can tell me where Kader is so I can kill him.
Then I looked,
...it turns out that girl is in the same situation as me.
In short, we have come across such a coincidence with Meryem,
...if I tell it to someone now, they will say...
''Let Agah turn around, stop, the world is that small.''
And I tell him...
''The world is not small, crime is big''
I guess everyone here knows me.
But let me explain it in a few words.
These murderers had a list in their hands.
There were nineteen names on this list.
Nineteen people, nineteen people.
Of these nineteen people, they kidnapped sixteen.
They disappeared, they disappeared. There are three of us left.
Two of them passed away.
They died of their own causes.
In the end, I was the only one left alive.
Now...
...how did we save ourselves from the people who kidnapped and destroyed them...
...how did we escape from their hands?
We gave money to them.
We gave money to these murderers. And that's how we survived.
But believe me...
...we have been very ashamed of what we did throughout our lives.
We were always ashamed.
There are empty graves here.
And I'm still alive...
I am very ashamed of this.
Does a person feel ashamed every time he breathes?
I am ashamed.
Then I had a child,
...I was very ashamed of him too.
We love you very much, uncle Abidin.
The ones who should really be ashamed are those who killed those 17 lives!
Gel.
They told us to forget.
They said you will forget.
And they thought we would forget it without shame.
But every time they say forget it...
...we remembered more.
Now here, with this monument,
...not only us, but also others will remember.
Everyone will remember.
There are 17 empty graves here. 17 open wounds.
And unless we are held accountable for our losses!
Unless the bones of these people are found.
Our wounds will never heal.
And these lands will always remain riddled with holes.
A person's relative disappears,
Three days pass and she waits for him to return.
Three years pass and she waits for him to call.
Thirty years pass,
...let me find your bones, he says!
That's what I say!
At least let me find my father's bones...
...don't let your bones ache anymore!
Everyone should know this very well!
We are here.
And whatever you do,
...we will never get lost!
Dilan Erdem!
We are here. Are you here too?
Here.
- Seyit Güven! - Here.
- Fahriye Güven! - Here.
- Remzi Yuksel! - Here.
- Victorious Lion! - Here.
- Saruhan Demiroğlu! - Here.
- Halil Karachay! - Here.
- Çetin Ertuk! - Here.
- Selime Özdemir. - Here.
- Mehmet İrfanoğlu. - Here.
- Fuat Erarslan! - Here.
- Kadir Dogan! - Here.
- Turgut Kefeci! - Here.
- İlhami Güral! - Here.
- Melih Derin! - Here.
- Süreyya Bozkaya! - Here.
- Tibetan Delusion! - Here.
At the core of all of these is the same darkness.
The missing, the unsolved, they all lead to the same darkness.
My son, Ateş Arbay...
...he no longer exists just because he was doing his duty, being a journalist. No.
(unintelligible speech)
We're looking for it, we're looking for it, it's nowhere to be found. Reach out!
What will I do, my child?
Give me some advice,
...where should I go, what should I do, who should I contact?
We will find it, auntie.
-...we will find it somehow! - Miss Meryem.
- Thank you, son. - Sorry. Miss Mary.
Mr. Agah!
But I told you, today is not a good day.
It's okay. I came anyway. I just want to ask you something.
Pardon.
Do you have the address of this Kader?
- Why, what will you do? - I will kill.
(breathing) Mr. Agah!
You obviously didn't understand what we were trying to do.
So don't tell me this,
...I hope I didn't hear about it either!
My son,
…didn't you just mention the names of these 17 souls one by one from the podium?
Will they not be held accountable? That's what I'm going to do!
Fariz, Mr. Agah is like this…
What happened? What happened?
- Come on, uncle. Come on, come on. - What happened?
- What happened? And what did I say? - Come, go, go.
- I'm asking something. - Come on, come on uncle, come on.
- I'm asking for an address. - Okay okay.
Well, I asked for an address.
- Come on, uncle, walk. - Oh, okay, don't push me.
I'm not pushing you, go ahead.
It's a shame, okay okay, I'm here okay.
Never again come to places where you are not invited.
God! God!
Heh!
Do you know the location of Destiny?
Uncle, I don't know.
But if I knew, I would tell you.
- Shh. Shh. - What?
I swear Agah, you have no other choice.
Open the glove compartment, there should be a key in there.
- Is this? - What! What!
Weren't you the apartment manager?
Which apartment?
Mebrure!
Oh Melek!
Oh, what have you prepared, in so much turmoil?
Oh, well done.
Well, I didn't make it, the neighbors did it and brought it.
Stuffed... My mother makes it very well.
Ramiz also loved it very much.
In other words, he would eat half a pot of stuffed vegetables in one sitting.
Do you know? I actually saw the deceased.
But it's been a while.
He came to the neighborhood to ask something from Hikmet.
I know I know.
- He wanted a gun. - What!
You made him look like you too.
Melek, look, I couldn't be a big brother to my brother.
I could neither hold his hand nor show him the way.
So he went and became a vagabond for three cents.
Then a guy came out and shot him, saying he was a bum to me.
It was my fault.
Because I left here.
My dear, can such a thing happen?
What to do there. Just because you left, is it possible?
Angel!
Just because I left,
...if you loved Hikmet, anything is possible.
So I'm gone.
The world has turned upside down.
- Come on, honey, come on. - We'll wait again.
Thanks.
- Should we buy a smaller one? - No dear, just this, just come on.
- Pardon! - Pardon!
- Hello! - Here you go.
My son, I live upstairs. Can you help me?
I couldn't get this to work.
- Trouble for you. - Give it to me, let me take a look.
- This one's battery is dead. - Really?
- Well, just put it on. - Let me put it on.
Heh... This place was a thing! It was a tavern.
That sign has legs.
- Isn't it? - Yes brother.
So what's happening now?
We sell fancy gadgets and stuff.
Fantasy.
Masallah. Yes. Well, eh?
Isn't it a bit shameful, in such a public place?
That sign outside or something. Uh, so.
There were no such things when we were young.
Well, people are looking for different things now. They are looking for new excitements.
If you need tools to get excited...
...so you're already dead. So leave these things alone.
What's the name of this?
Full Erotic Shop.
Be my guest!
At least you could do it properly, couldn't you find a Turkish name?
How can I know!
Land of Lust, etc!
- Heh, it's opened. - Once it's opened, it's good.
Oh, would you take a look at his thing?
- For what? - You know, the one who calls, the one you seek,
...it's always written there! I am now...
- Let me see right away, brother. -...I don't remember, old phone.
I swear there is nothing in your call log. Or deleted.
Let me take a look at your thing. Let me look at your guide.
- Pretty odd! - How strange?
- There's only one trick! - One trick!
Give this a call. Allah! Allah!
Oh, live.
Has fate come?
It's here, commander.
Good good. Pour him some tea and let's drink it together.
Welcome, Destiny.
No kissing hands?
Pushshhhh... My daughter..
Pshhh...
- Damn, stop! What the hell is going on? - Where is Ulaş?
Answer, answer? What did you do to the child?
- Where to Reach? - Which one is Ulaş?
- Where is Ulaş? - Damn!
Who knows you best in this world?
What kind of a person he really is...
What you can do...
What are you afraid of...
Who knows what and how long you can endure?
My second...
Is it your brother...
Your friends...
Or is it your love...
None of them.
Because in this world, your partner in crime knows you the most.
Only he knows who he is.
I know.
Because I also have a partner in crime.
I mean, maybe I'm not an innocent, but.
At least I'm not alone in this world.