(children's voices)
Actually, sometimes I can't understand it at all, I wonder how a person can...
Does he think about people he doesn't know more than himself?
Teacher, you would give your photo.
After all, a person doesn't know anything other than himself so he can think about others.
If he doesn't have it, it's his own trouble, his own pain, his own pleasure.
Sorry, can we hurry? I have to go back to school.
Come on, if you didn't know, his parents, his children, his wife.
But someone else whose name he doesn't even know yet
or the one who lives thousands of kilometers away from himself.
Even if one lives to the fullest, why does one think about those who are not like him?
Why does he value someone he doesn't even know? - What are you doing with the child?
What is it to him? Isn't it? What's wrong with you?
Baby goat!
Mary! Come on, girl, go to bed.
But some of them are. It's getting weird.
He says that no matter how many people there are in this world...
All of their problems are mine.
Even if he knows, no one thinks about him.
Yet he still stubbornly thinks about it all.
Then what happens?
(incomprehensible speech)
One night, someone he doesn't know knocks on his door and pulls the trigger.
However, in most murders in this world, the killer knows the victim personally, right?
But, when a person starts to think about people he has never met...
The murderer is someone he doesn't even know.
They don't say it's an unknown perpetrator for nothing.
Because the victim does not know the killer.
If you say the murderer, he doesn't know the victim either.
Here you go, another unknown
(children's voices)
If you load the big ship with so much uncertainty, where else will it go?
You, me, all of us can only go to the bottom of the unknown.
Good evening.
Shh
Come on, thank you.
I think we found it!
Who's this?
(Do not breathe)
There are so many disasters in this life...
You never know how you will react until it happens to you.
Ms. Safiye!
Guys!
For example, a man comes across and...
If he said he would kill your whole family first and then you...
Whatever you do? Would you go to the police?
Or do you act like something like this never happened and try to forget it?
Well... if someone killed your cat
what do you do then?
I remembered something.
No matter how much it hurt me at that moment, revenge was obviously not enough...
On top of that, I wanted to start a war.
So just when I need it,
I remembered that I had a huge arsenal.
Mackerel street. Mebrure Apartment. At number 8.
Namaste. How can I help?
Who are you? What are you doing here? I had my things?
What did you have?
I say it's me...
How dare they sell my house! So where are my guns?
Mr. Agah! Hello.
Hello, I didn't recognize you.
Can we talk a little?
Reason?
Is he following me?
Yes.
Which incompetent person took this photo?
- Its horizon line is crooked! Is it possible to frame like this? - Mr. Agah!
Heh.
Don't you know this person now?
No I do not know! I don't know you either!
I told you. My name is Meryem, I am a lawyer.
Are you the lawyer for this?
- Mr. Agah... - Uhh..
Very simple. We are after this man. He is after you too.
Now when we learned this, we did some research on you.
Then we learned that you went and gave a statement to the police.
Well, how do you know these?
Where did you hear that? No, I went to the police, what did I say?
It's not important.
- We want to help you. - Uhh..
But first you need to tell us the truth.
Huh?
- Mr. Agah! - Huh?
Do you really not remember who the people you killed were?
I don't remember, my son, I don't remember! I have Alzheimer's too.
I said this too
I said I have Alzheimer's disease and I don't remember, but he didn't believe me.
He also threatened me, you bastard!
No, he killed my daughter, or my family.
He went and killed my cat, that bastard. His unscrupulous son is unscrupulous!
So that's why he came out.
Why?
To take revenge on you.
What revenge?
Maybe to silence.
- Mr. Agah? - Huh?
Did you leave that confession unfinished on purpose?
To blackmail?
Blackmailing who?
To these people.
Who are they? I don't know them.
Really? Let me tell you this, Mr. Agah.
These men will not leave you behind.
Until yesterday, no one knew this man's face.
No one knew whether he was dead or alive.
But then he risked everything. It emerged thirty years later.
I wonder why?
What should I know?
Could it be because you went and gave a statement to the police?
Otherwise, why would he come here and chase you?
Maybe you're not that innocent after all. Huh?
But maybe, one day, you decide to remember. You can call me.
Maybe we can help you too.
Can I have them now?
Of course you can have it. Now, my lady, if I may ask...
Can you tell me who they are and what they are?
I think you know who they are better than I do.
Because a person knows the person he betrayed.
Mr. Agah! Can I have it please?
Mr. Agah! Mr. Agah, Mr. Agah, what are you doing?
Aah! Agah bey!
Meryem, let it go, let it go.
(breath)
The cat is also thirsty.
Oh my darling cat.
What happened to you?
When did you leave me and go away?
Look, this is Ms. Safiye.
I always said, take me to Mr. Münir, take me to Mr. Münir, my child brought me.
You will now sleep side by side.
Take care of each other, okay?
I couldn't look at you, forgive me.
But you, take care of each other.
Bu ne ya?
What's this?
Did you kill my cat?
What cat bro? What are you talking about?
Get in.
- Isn't your name Fahri? - Yes.
Are you the night watchman here? Really?
So I am.
What?
Put that gun down.
The guy says to me, you killed my brother.
I say I didn't do it, he says you did.
I say I don't remember, he says remember.
Then someone else comes and says you betrayed them.
Who are you that I should betray you? Who are you?
Look brother, tell me how you found me and I will answer your questions.
I found it however I found it. What's it to you?
You killed my cat? My cat!
Well, what can you do, it's destiny.
What the hell fate? You hanged my cat.
That's okay. Destiny!
Are you kidding me? Huh?
Bu ne ya?
Our guests would come here. While I was waiting for them, I saw that Agah had arrived.
He wants you.
Well done Agah.
This is what the adversary will be like. Well, I didn't expect it from you at all.
You know a lot about these things.
But I guess you know my name by now.
"Fate" is now written on your forehead.
That's mine.
You leave him alone and answer me. You killed my cat, didn't you?
Once again, I will bring this to your nose, this is a...
But first, you will leave my family behind...
Or is this Fahri standing in front of me?
Don't tire yourself out, Agah. Don't bother trying to get Fahri to talk.
He wouldn't say a word if you ripped his liver out. Shoot Fahri directly!
Either hit your forehead from the roof or go back home.
Look at me!
He hung up. Take it.
What did he say?
What kind of person are you! What kind of insidious conversations are these?
He is an enemy, his heart has been ripped out, what are you doing?
Is it that easy to take a life? This is human, human. Life!
First of all, a man first thinks about what comes out of his mouth.
He thinks first, then speaks.
But whether this is Destiny or what, the guy has a habit of saying the first thing that comes to his mind.
What did he say?
What will he say, Mr. Fahri, my brother, he said this.
Ahh! is it okay now? So is this it? Shoot and shoot.
Isn't it a shame?
Who knows, you have spouses, friends and loved ones. Heh, isn't it a shame?
Moreover, you obviously have a law. Who knows how many years he's known you?
But no, just pull and shoot. Is this it?
Bad manners. He doesn't know the manners of talking on the phone anyway.
Don't interrupt someone like that while the other person is talking.
( laugh )
How dare you grin!
- Cure! - What happened to Deva?
First the cat, then Deva!
Deva!
First, you put my foot in a shoe. You're making me rush.
I forget later.
I'll get right to the point!
I'm an alcoholic!
I am a woman who has never been able to hold down any job she has ever worked for.
I am a child with a father with Alzheimer's and fifty problems.
I am a wife who constantly fights with her husband!
I am all of these!
Or rather, I was! Until it comes back to life!
So what brought me back to life?
Of course ''Dog Killer''!
Come on! Come on! Pick up that phone!
Why did I survive? Why did I survive?
Why did I survive?
Here's to writing this.
(enthusiastic voices)
Oh no, father, where is this coming from?
No, something happened. Something happened to television.
So I decided to look at the antenna, so I went up to the roof for two minutes.
Well, we have cable broadcasting, daddy, there is no antenna up there.
No! Well, it doesn't exist, I couldn't find it either.
It doesn't exist! What can I say? Please call this Deva so I can hear the child's voice.
Oh daddy, evening, evening...
So I don't understand why you want Deva, I will call.
I felt like hearing the boy's voice, call me, let's talk to the boy.
See, he felt it too.
What did I feel? What happened, did something happen to Deva?
Well, okay, don't panic, we called but couldn't reach you...
- Zuhal is talking about him, so we couldn't reach him. - Well, what else?
Well, he calls us, he is now up in the mountains, in the hills, the phone has no reception, I know that.
How comfortable are you, Ertan! How comfortable you are.
- No, daddy, don't worry. - Hey dad, there is nothing to worry about.
What do you mean, there is nothing to worry about? Don't people care about their children?
- Is this how we raised you? - Yes.
What, how yes?
Dad, for God's sake, let me know what I will tell you from now on.
Also, how can you sell number 8 below without asking me?
You also sold it to gymnasts. They are stamping on people's heads.
Can a house be sold to a gymnast?
They're not gymnasts, dad. That's the yoga center.
Anyway, one has to ask.
I say, "Dad, how can I ask you? You were sick."
They declared me as a compulsory guardian, and I dealt with a thousand tons of work.
No court, no committee report, I don't know what...
Dad, I paid for that nursing home for four and a half years.
- Do you know how expensive it is? - Huh!
I didn't know what to do, so I had to sell the flat.
You did well.
Okay okay okay. Could you calm down a little? OK, calm down.
Why didn't you take me with you?
A person takes care of his father at home. That's all I got sick.
It wouldn't cost that much.
I can't believe it, can you hear what he's saying?
Does he hear what, wait a minute, who didn't want me at home?
Are you? Is this? Heh? Which of you didn't want it?
What are you shouting about, the girl will wake up?
Aahh!...Ya Deva sen geldin mi ya?
Son, why don't you answer the phone, we are scared to death.
Deva, son, when did you come?
It's been an hour since we arrived. I knocked on the door, but no one opened it.
An hour?
Dad, you were out for two minutes.
You left him alone and gave keys to everyone?
Heh! Is this a passing inn?
You said, "I'm going to go crazy, father, child, I'm curious, I'm curious."
The boy appeared in front of you, is this your problem now?
Dude, call and ask, we're dying of curiosity!
Ok. I will ask the real question.
Look at me, where is it? Is there someone? Is there a girl somewhere?
(stretch)
Hello! I'm Fatoş.
We are married!
That's why you wanted money from me?
Well, getting married is not easy, mom.
Heh! Here you go, light it up!
What will we say to Fahri's wife? The woman will be ruined.
I'll talk..
What do you say?
I'll say don't involve the police, we'll handle it.
So, won't the woman want to see her husband one last time?
Aren't they married? Has he seen as much as he can see?
Well, won't this man have a tombstone?
Hikmet, green came.
Come, come, come, come...come. Okay whoop!
You haven't changed at all, Destiny?
Haven't I changed? If you say this too, Hikmet.
Wisdom!
Wisdom! If I hadn't changed. Just to keep my brother's blood on the ground...
Will I come all the way from here to take revenge? If only in the past...
He wouldn't care at all.
Yes.
What would I always say?
Fatality.
I'd say it's fate, right?
But when a person gets older, he becomes different. So, out of the blue, past memories come to mind.
Wisdom! Tell me, what is revenge?
You will only feel it, your mind will be on yesterday, and you will want to go and take revenge.
What a great weakness, isn't it, Hikmet?
I am no longer the old Kader you know.
I am a weak man. Weak.
If I weren't weak, would I try so hard for my brother?
If my conscience didn't hurt, would I go and slaughter that cat?
If I were not a sensitive man, I would go and kill everyone's children...
Why should I try to kill?
Wisdom! (mumbling prayer)
- Alhamdulillah.. - I know.
Mary! Are you serious?
- Is he really here? - Yes.
Just relax.
Look, we have been patient and waited all these years.
That's why we won't rush now and make the wrong decision.
Otherwise, I am in such a situation...
When I saw the photos of the man...
I'm trying very hard not to go and grab his throat.
But we won't do that now. Is it ok?
ok
There is something we need to be sure about now.
What is it?
Mom! Don't do this, what would happen?
Look, you came all this way, take a look at this photo, let's go home.
No.
Come on mom, open your eyes.
I mean, if there was another way, would I ever make you suffer this torment?
But not. No, there is no other way.
You're the only one who saw this man.
Didn't you say that he always comes into my dreams?
I see the face of this guy called Kader. Please..
What happens if I can't? I won't be able to.
Mom! My mother! Look, we need to be sure. Heh?
Did this man come to our house?
What happens?
This man is the only one, he didn't take my father away, mom.
Well, he didn't just take her away.
Do you know how many people are like you?
What happened to my child, what happened to my brother...
They have been crying bitterly for thirty years asking what happened to my husband. Mother, what if I become a sacrifice?
Ahh.
Yes.
Daddy, where are we going to run away at this hour?
There's no need to run away, girl, there's no running away, where did running come from?
Daddy, wait a minute, can you stop? It's father time.
- Daddy, wait a minute, my dear. - Put your paws down, girl.
Dad, where are we going to go at this hour, for God's sake?
To where? Where are we going at this hour?
Why are you walking around the house in your underwear?
Go put some clothes on. We'll find a place to go, there are lots of hotels.
Should we call the doctor?
Daddy, please sit down and let's talk.
Just so you know, I don't do anything without taking my daughter and grandchild on vacation.
It is not clear how much of my life is left here, while I am ready...
Thank you dad, please don't say that.
- You come with me. - Heh!
- Come on, come on, come on, come on - Should I call an ambulance?
Should we call an ambulance? Ambulance ambulance.
- Fatos! Remedy! Let's call an ambulance, he's not well. - Come on. My daughter.
Now I'm taking this medicine, girl, I'm reborn.
God gave me a second chance, a second life.
While you were there shouting at each other in the evening, I was looking at the sky like this.
Suddenly a falling star fell. So I made a wish.
I said, Agah, don't make the mistakes you made in your old life again. Don't do it!
Then you came to my mind, your childhood.
When you were a child, you always cried, Dad, why don't you take us on vacation?
Take us on vacation. I said that the new Agah would take his daughter on vacation.
The old Agah did not release it, the new one will.
No matter what he does, he doesn't stop even for a second, finds his way, takes his daughter on vacation.
He made his daughter cry once, he will never make her cry again.
Get ready, we are going on vacation.
( laugh )
To where ?
Daddy, where did you find that?
My daughter, the car has been renewed, new car, new toy, new decoration, how?
In your words, isn't it cool?
- But the car is like a beast! - Oh, that's okay, but still go slow.
Don't regret letting me sit behind the wheel.
Grandpa, I'm looking at the mirrors. If you want to get some sleep.
What am I going to sleep, you sleep. Oh, don't sleep, don't sleep!
- Daddy! - Heh?
- I'm looking at the photos. - Heh?
I think I found a great hotel heh, you will love it.
My daughter, our goal is to be together as a family. Isn't it? Look how beautiful.
It's like he was born into Deva. My lion is up and coming.
Actually, I wasn't going to tell you, but something happened and that's why we came.
(incomprehensible speech)
- Destiny. - Sir.
Sıtkı is the friend I told you about. He gave us the news.
- Heh, no no no. - It's a great honor for me.
Thank you brother, thank you Sıtkı.
Was it worth it?
What bro?
How much did you sell this face for?
What to sell bro?
Who did you sell me to, Sıtkı?
There is something wrong, brother Kader, I didn't do anything.
Your man doesn't say that, but Sıtkı. You put Destiny up for auction.
Which man am I?
Damn son of a *****.
Why did you shoot the man, my son? Heh! How will we find out now who he sold the photos to?
Hikmet, don't be angry, don't be angry. That's how these kids are.
My son, come and see. Come.
Aaahh..
That's what this mafia is like.
He is either stupid or a fraud.
That's why I've always been against it.
This shit called mafia.
How? Did a thief break into the house?
I don't know, I guess.
We were outside, we came back home, they broke the door.
Well, they didn't take anything, but they turned the house upside down.
They also wrote something on the living room wall.
What did they write?
They were drunk or something, probably high or something.
Tell me, son, what did they write?
That was nonsense!
My son, tell me what they wrote?
Destiny cannot be prevented.
God God!
Maybe they were just children... Of course, Fatoş got quite angry.
He said, "I can't stay in this house anymore."
You know, you were always saying, come and see your grandfather...
So we went out and here we are.
Oh my baby, oh my dear Deva, you got it right, I will be a paragliding instructor...
I don't know what will happen, there was shit on the paraglider.
Mommy, what does it matter now? I'm telling you someone broke into the house.
Daddy! Okay, I've done my job, we can go.
Before you leave, son, do this job.
What about dad, you took us out in such a hurry, I mean, should I pee my pants?
Oh Ertan!