Everything in this life has an end.
Some people sit quietly and wait for that end to come to them.
Some people get up and walk.
He goes to the end on his own.
I made a decision.
Since I started this story,
I will bring the end to it.
This story is not another one,
I will finish it.
Agah Beyoğlu…
Tell me.
Officer... I did it...
All those people… I killed them.
One by one…
All…
Do not do that! How many times have I told you!
What the hell, he's having fun!
Okay, but his blood pressure will rise.
(unintelligible speech)
Especially my wife will take care of her. Thank you.
I mean, it was the bathroom, the toilet, etc.
He will always handle it.
That's why we won't need an extra babysitter, thank you.
Well, whatever you want.
Well! Then if you sign your release papers…
- Come on, let's go to my room. - Ok.
When I first walked into that nursing home, I was faking it.
It was as if the disease had progressed and I had become disconnected from the world.
The best place to hide after all those murders,
It was a disease called Alzheimer's.
But apparently the trick turned out to be real.
I was trapped in my hiding place... I didn't know it.
Baba!
Father. Get up dad, come on, we're going home.
What happened?
What's the part of this? Heh!
What if, my dear, we could go to a hotel?
As I said, it is very important for Ertan to be in an environment he knows.
So there needs to be something around him that will jog his memory.
Hah! Father! Isn't it my mother?
Mebrure? Did you remember?
How can the man remember? For God's sake!
Father!
Now look!
You will drink this, okay?
It'll all be over, let's see.
Drink, drink, drink… Okay.
Baba!
You know, you left me at boarding school!
I was so little!
Do not worry about it!
I won't leave you.
Is it ok?
Come on. Look at my mother!
Saturn!
Come on dad.
What happened?
My love, this man hasn't said a word for years.
He doesn't react to anything other than Tom Jones!
Well! I don't understand how you think you will get better.
No, now how did this biochemist give you this medicine!
In other words, it is not even clear whether it is a medicine or not, it has not been tested, it has not been made, it has not been looked at!
Maybe it has a side effect, don't you ever think about it?
Where did it go?
He is wandering around his house.
DAY 1
DAY 17
Daddy!
Have you ever come back from the dead?
I'm back…
But where did I turn?
Turns out that was the real issue.
Ok, I came back to life...
Where exactly did I end up in that life?
What did I do!
I forgot to give water to Münir Bey!
Mr. Munir! Where are you, my son Münir!
Aah! Zuhal!
No, what are you doing here? When did you come?
Dad, do you know me?
Do you know what it means? Are you kidding me girl?
I'm looking for Münir Bey. Have you seen him? Tell him!
Mr. Munir! There was a water container here!
The child had a water bowl, but now he doesn't have a water bowl.
Mr. Münir, where are you, son!
Was this left in the bathroom?
Don't let it be locked! Munir!
- Thank God! Daddy! - Come on! Who is there!
- Daddy! Do you remember me? - Who is there! Mr. Münir, did you stay there?
Girl, what are you saying? What does it mean to remember!
Well, it worked, huh! The medicine worked!
Hayda!
Ertan, my father knows me.
What are you doing here?
- He recognized you too! Thank God. - What's up, Ertan? You wouldn't come to your hometown!
Wait a minute! How did you get in!
Did you have the key too?
Daddy!
Girl, what happened, why are you crying?
Did something happen to Deva?
Deva, he said! Deva says!
What should I say, should I say Mahmut? The child's name is Deva, right?
Wait a minute, could you have left the door open? Ertan!
Did you leave the door open and he ran away, Mr. Münir?
- My daddy! - Look, if you did something like this. We change the cones accordingly!
Okay okay okay. Nothing, okay. Mr. Munir!
That biochemist of yours will win the Nobel Prize, for sure!
Mr. Munir!
Dad, do you really remember everything?
My daughter!
- When and what did I forget! - Heh!
What was your surname, daddy?
Are you kidding me, are you making fun of me, son?
Is there any other Beyoğlu left in Beyoğlu other than me?
- Mr. Munir! Mr. Munir! Where is this kid? - This is a miracle, I swear it is a miracle.
- Dad! Let me ask you something too.. - Mr. Münir!
- What? - Dad, what were you doing?
- Where did you retire from? - Girl, for God's sake, go and find another entertainment for yourself.
What were you doing, Daddy? Where did you retire from?
Grandmother ? How where? Say well!
Where is dad?
Well, I was doing something!
What were you doing?
Courthouse clerk?
I studied law, what's the point!
You haven't finished university, daddy. You left when you married my mother.
How many years did you say?
Twenty seven.
Twenty-seven years! Was I a courthouse clerk for twenty-seven years?
There is no such thing, there is something wrong. No such thing!
Baba!
Heh!
Look! Look now, look at this photo.
Look, this is the Ardıçhan courthouse.
Is it ok?
Look, you know what's here?
Look, for example, these photos were taken in Silopi.
Look who's around you? All your friends and colleagues from the courthouse.
Now you tell me that I have spent my entire life in civil service,
That's what you're telling me!
No, daddy, it's not like that, but you were very happy,
- So you loved what you did. - How do you know?
Heh!. How do you know I'm happy?
I mean, you looked like that, daddy.
So I was deceiving myself!
Dad, look at it this way, you're getting angry, annoyed, etc.
What else would you do?
I don't know, girl! I don't know what I was going to do!
I don't know! I don't remember! Who was I, what was I, what was I doing!
No way!
First of all, I am a poet-spirited man!
Is he a poet?
''I am a walnut tree in Gülhane park''
''Neither you nor the police are aware of this.''
If I were not a poet, how would I remember Nazım Hikmet? Heh?
I don't even remember what I do yet.
Daddy, please don't do such things, take care of yourself!
Until yesterday, you didn't remember who we were.
Would you look at yourself now? Please! Poems, poems.
Aah, you are the only person in this world who had Alzheimer's and recovered.
Think about this, I ask!
I got better, but what happened? No, what happened now, I knew, I learned, what happened?
If you had left me like that.
Look, please don't say that, dad, I really feel sorry for you.
Mr. Münir is not there anyway! What did you do to the cat?
Where is this cat?
Dad, there is no cat!
What do you mean, how can it not exist?
Let me die so I can be saved!
What kind of world is this, what kind of life is this?
Münir Bey is not there either! Let me die and be saved!
Daddy!
He lost consciousness.
Daddy! Father!
- He shut down, he shut down, his consciousness turned off. - Daddy!
Dad, daddy. Dad, are you okay?
You were already going to kill yourself.
Who knows how unhappy you were.
If only you had squeezed your head!
You couldn't do it, could you?
Because you were afraid.
You were afraid of death.
(laugh)
You coward!
You must also be afraid of being hungry! Ass!
That's why you went and became a clerk, right?
But I'm not afraid!
Do you know why?
Because I am Agah Beyoğlu.
I have to leave immediately. I have a job.
Where to dad?
I'm going to do something I've never done before!
What is it?
I will live my life!
What will you do? How will you live your life?
I have two questions for you.
One! Where's your mother's car?
Two! Which donkey made me wear these!
Who are you? Who are you?
- Oh dad, it's so beautiful. - So sweet.
AGAIN
Father! Oh dad! Ugh!
Father! Wait!
- Oh Ertan, why don't you stop it? - I'm paying for it, Zuhal!
(laugh)
(nida)
(unintelligible speech)
(enthusiastic voices)
- Ahhh!
(unintelligible speech)
Brother, don't do it!
Ahhh! Ahhh! Ahhh!
(unintelligible speech)
Ahhh!
Officer! Officer! Officer!
- Are you okay, uncle!
I killed a man!
What do you say, uncle?
I killed so many people!
I say murderer! I'm a killer!
Chief, take a look, this says something.
Did something happen, uncle?
(Mumbling)
Well, you don't have a criminal record either, uncle.
But I'm just telling you, I hit that much, I say!
Why don't you believe me?
Okay uncle, okay, he will come now, you can tell him.
Who will come?
Come on, Mr. Prosecutor.
You go out.
- Now you remember that you shot someone. -Yes.
But you don't know who you are, do you?
No, I don't remember.
Why did you shoot these people, do you remember that?
No, I don't remember that either.
Ah! I! I forgot something!
What?
Is there any head left?
Am the Alzheimer var.
That's why I don't remember.
- Alzheimer's? - Yes!
Oh my God!
Understood, uncle.
Well, but wait a minute! I remember their faces!
I remember where I hit!
Even what did I tell them, what did they say to me...
I remember all of these.
For example, let me tell you this.
Well, for example, we are in a narrow street at night.
For example, that's Beyoğlu for sure.
I guess it's one of the back streets of Istiklal Avenue or something.
Now I'm standing in the middle of the road, these are coming.
- How many people are these? - Three people.
- One street... Beyoğlu... Three people...
What happens next?
Oh! Cut out the shape, what the hell is this!
Tub type!
Are you mafia, son?
Shh, wait, he's saying something, look! What?
I say are you mafia?
This is crazy!
Are you high? Heh?
Are you looking for trouble at night? F*ck off!
Stop, stop! Open your face!
Come on, come on, walk, we'll go to Sıtkı's place!
Who did you say?
Whose place were they going to?
A man called Sıtkı. They said they were going to Sıtkı's place.
I guess he is one of them, he is also the mafia.
How do you know that these are mafia?
They said it themselves! You already know their type!
They wore their coats and jackets so darkly.
No, I was already very angry at that moment!
And when someone says something to me!
I got really upset.
What is he saying?
A****** the fucking clown..
I said, "Are you a mafia, my son?"
Damn! We are mafia, what happens?
Good morning my baby! Here you go mafia.
This! This was it. I killed this!
There were two other people with him. I killed them too.
Leave that alone, did you hear this story from someone!
From whom will I hear it?
I'm telling you that I did it myself. Where do I come up with such things?
What did you shoot them with?
Well! But a gun!
Something like this?
Oh no! It's not like that, it has a magazine.
There was no sound from the gun.
So it was coming… It was such a very faint sound.
Of course! There is a silencer on the barrel, of course very little sound comes from it.
Do you know this woman?
No, I couldn't make it out. Who is this?
Are you the one who killed the dog?
Why should I kill the dog? Am I a sadist?
How can I kill animals, cats and dogs!
I tell you that I shot a human, neither a human nor a dog!
Why are you telling this story?
Well! I don't know, it just came to my mind for a moment. I said, I mean, what have I done?
I swear I was afraid of myself!
You are saying something like this...
Anyone who does what you say will stay in prison for life. Are you aware?
Yes! I don't know, so how do I know!
It just came to my mind, I said it, but I never thought about it.
For life... Well, of course, what would happen?
Dear prosecutor, his family has arrived. The man was sick. Alzheimer's
He had been missing since the evening... His daughter and son-in-law were looking for him.
What should we do?
Mr. Agah! You have Alzheimer's.
Yes.
In some of the stories you tell, I think they are all imaginary.
You are dreaming.
What can i say! God give healing.
- For God's sake, don't make me go crazy at night, look, I'm crazy, please don't do this at night. - I told you it wouldn't work,
- How many times have I said let's not return from Australia?
- So, are you sick of Australia now? - Well, I am sick of it.
- I took you by force, Ertan!
- I took him by force. - That's fine.
- Look what can I do, look at this situation!
-Am I the only one responsible?
Am I?
You would take care of me like a father, my son!
Of course I wanted to believe. And I wanted it so much.
Ohh, I said, it was all a dream! I didn't kill anyone.
How people deceive themselves.
But even worse…
That night, while I was telling about those murders, it turns out I woke up a monster.
Sir, prosecutor!
Sitki!
How are you?
It's fine, thank you.
Now listen carefully!
I will give you a name, and there will be no creditors left between us.
We will close the entire account, is that understood?
Hey, you're going to name a name big enough to close the account, right, prosecutor?
Well, tell me!
We found the person who killed Ramiz.
Which Ramiz?
Sence?
Hikmet brother is not Nevra. Someone else. A guy we don't know at all.
I even sent you the video now.
The guy gives such details, that's for sure.
So, what should I do now, well, if you want, I can finish the job immediately, let me handle it tonight.
Well, because his address is known.
No, just stop!
Let me first take a look at the video you sent.
Brother! If you don't mind, let me ask you something.
- Is Destiny really alive?
We finally found your brother's killer.
Only Destiny, the man says I have Alzheimer's...
That's why I remember only this much.
The prosecutor told Sıtkı that he was a really sick man.
So the head is gone.
That's why it's not worth it, bro.
Don't get involved.
Let's handle this here and get it over with.
You have already been patient in the hands of the infidel for 30 years...
Well, now…. Don't get up and come for this... isn't it?
Someone spreads a news story and the nation becomes aware of it….
Do not open old notebooks out of the blue.
Now everyone knows you are dead...
I'm sending you the video.
Well, officer, my son...
I shoot them, they die, I feel like I'm reborn!
I mean, while they are writhing in pain on the ground, I feel like laughing.
It's not possible! But it is!
Well, officer, my son...
I shoot them, they die, I feel like I'm reborn!
I mean, while they are writhing in pain on the ground, I feel like laughing.
(unintelligible speech)
Look, let's agree from the beginning. Okay, your father is starting to get better, he's starting to get better.
Okay, we can hire a woman and that's it.
Please let's be in Sydney before New Year's Eve..
We postponed all our work thinking that we would come, it can't happen like that.
I don't want to be late any longer.
Otherwise, let me know my conference settings here.
There are already many offers from Istanbul.
Oh Ertan, don't you even think about me?
As your husband, of course I think so.
But I mean, as your manager, I have to think about work, too, my love.
Ms. Safiye? Where are you?
Come on, it's food time.
It's breakfast time.
Ms. Safiye?
Come on, eat your food...
Let's call Münir Bey. Münir Bey is missing.
Heh !
Ms. Safiye!
Heh!
Heehhh! Are you here!
I said, this too has disappeared, like Mr. Münir, yes.
Allah bless! Come.
Baba!
What's up, girl? I am giving food to Ms. Safiye.
Okay, come on, we will have breakfast, you will take your medicine.
Okay okay. Okay I am coming.
Ms. Safiye!
Oh, you finally came out! Grandpa, how are you?
How can I be, Deva, I'm not well.
You look very good. You are like a monster!
It's because of the tool, that's why the tool makes it look defective.
(LAUGH)
Mom! And can you send me some more money?
Deva ..
Dear Deva, we have just sent money, what kind of money is this, for no reason!
Dad, Beyoğlu has changed a lot, hasn't it? Look at this situation!
Ertan!
Ertan, can you take a look? Ertan!
Deva wants money.
I'm a cure, I called and called but he didn't answer.
I just sent you money, son. I sent new money.
There is no one left in Beyoğlu to change.
Look at this situation!
It seems like people are not walking, they are crushing each other.
Beyoğlu is finished.
Agah Beyoğlu is also finished.
(korna session)
Hih! Car!
How many days has he been there, no one cares!
Are you Alzheimer's or me?
A huge car, how can one forget?
Baba!
Please Attention!.. Dear passengers…
For your safety, do not cross the yellow line on the platforms!
(english announcement)
(unintelligible speech)
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
Excuse me, what is this card?
This thing is an elderly card. Free. The metro is free.
- May I look? -Of course.
Free senior card.
Well, we are old now.
(laugh)
Yes.
I fell asleep and woke up! Everything has changed!
The world has changed.
Yes, it is, it is a completely different country.
Yaa!
I've been out for a long time...
Huh!
So I say, where is that old Istanbul!
Right, where!
But I don't remember.
Alzheimer's was fixed.
I take medicine.
I guess it sounds good, so…
For example, I remembered something.
I remembered where I parked the car, I'm going to pick it up now.
- Beautiful, beautiful, so beautiful, so beautiful. - Oh!
I remember their phone numbers.
What more do you want?
I didn't remember before.
But I don't remember myself, bro.
Who was I, what kind of person was I? I have no idea.
My daughter tells me.
Here, you were like this, you were like that, you did this, you did that.
I was amazed!
What can I do like that! Exit!
Then I got angry at people, I mean.
Then I got so nervous that, well, I started shooting them all, one by one.
In a dream, I guess.
It's a subconscious thing.
So, you see, it's gone too, it's gone.
There is nothing left like reasoning or anything.
But, I'm trying to remember this.
What kind of person was I, what did I want in life, what did I do?
If I understand him.
Can a person live without remembering himself, brother! Can such a thing happen?
That's why I'm taking medications.
But I don't know, maybe that's it. This much.
As Yunus Emre says: "There is a self within me."
Maybe there is no other Agah inside.
Was!
How would you know?
There is, there is, trust me.
There is another Agah inside you.
(laugh)
That's why I came to you.
How?
I said, if he is on this medicine, he will come to his senses!
Let me kill your family first.
What are you saying? Is he crazy or what, go ahead.
- Listen to me, listen to me for a minute. - What am I going to listen to, don't talk nonsense, go away.
- Listen, listen to me. - Oh, go ahead.
- Look! Let me tell you what will happen. - Oh God, get away from me.
Go! What's it to you? Whatever happens, what does it matter to you? Go ahead.
Whoever is around you,
Everyone you love will die one by one.
You will die last.
Are you sick or what, go away!
You know, you say, who am I?
You know those murders you told the police about?
You are the man who killed those people.
Don't you dare go to the police!
They let you in. Your family stays outside.
I will kill them again, but it would be a pity if you couldn't see them.
How do you know that I went to the police and what I told them? Who are you?
I am the man who will punish you, Agah Effendi.
What's the punishment? I didn't kill anyone, it was all a dream.
The prosecutor said so anyway!
Your punishment starts from now on. You will suffer, there is no solution!
What punishment, what did I do?
That daughter, son-in-law, grandchild, all of you...
I will bury it in the ground in such a way...
Even if the whole world comes, they won't be able to find it.
From where? I didn't do anything!
You killed my brother.
What's the point, why should I kill your brother?
I don't know. You will remember.
What will I remember?
Your treatment is going a little slow, let me speed it up.
- You'll remember this, right! - What is this?
This is the biggest crime you've ever committed!
Personal…
You made this my brother's destiny, Agah Effendi.
But now, do you know what is written on your forehead?
Kader.
Is it?
Sorry uncle!
Dur!
What will I remember!
What does it matter?
It's a relationship!
What will I remember!