(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
We all have different places we want to go
But first, we need
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
Sparks fly, no limit
This is where it starts
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
Are your dreams still pure?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
Still, all of us
In the middle of an adventure
All of us, I tell you travelers
No such thing as a pointless fight
When random contexts
Start to make sense on their own
The threads of time are spun back together
The world keeps changing along with us
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
Now, explain to us!
KING COBRA ASSASSINATED
The truth... behind this shocking news!
After returning to Kamabakka Queendom,
Sabo started recounting about the incident
that took place
in the Holy Land Mary Geoise.
It's an emergency! Someone trespassed
into the Land of the Gods!
I saw Saint Rosward and his son Charlos...
I will save... Kuma-san at any cost!
Stop!
Only King Cobra is permitted
an audience with the Five Elders.
But...
Cobra-sama is not in good health.
Stand back.
Cobra-sama...
This won't take long,
but I think it'll be boring to
just wait outside.
I need you to guard Vivi.
She's still so mischievous,
and I can't stop worrying about her.
"The Holy Land in Tumult!
Sai and Leo's Full-Power Blow!"
HOLY LAND MARY GEOISE
You bastard!
Give me back the keys!
You're Sabo, right?!
What? You're...
Jewelry Bonney?!
If you know me, that'll save us time.
We might have the same goal.
There are intruders in the guardroom!
They stole the keys
to the slaves' collars! Catch them!
I heard that Kuma-san had a daughter.
I've always been keeping tabs on
the Revolutionary Army's news.
So I trust you guys!
Please save my father!
Yeah, that's what we're here for.
-What?!
-Karasu!
Yeah.
Take these keys! And tell this
to Morley and the others, too.
Once you unlock Kuma-san
and the slaves' collars,
go straight back to the headquarters.
Your mission is complete!
What about you, Sabo?
I'll follow you once I finish my business!
Okay. But be careful!
What are you gonna do next, Bonney?
I'm gonna go to Egghead.
All by yourself?
Yeah.
Are you gonna be okay?
That's the World Government's territory.
I've got to ask Vegapunk how to restore
my father's sense of self!
That's what I set out to sea for!
Is there a way to restore
his sense of self?
Even if there isn't, I'll make him do it!
If he can't...
There they are!
This way! Hurry up!
What?
Where are they?!
No one's here!
That's strange. I saw someone here...
Th-Thanks.
Hey, they reduced the number of guards
in this tower again.
Even though
there's so much space to cover.
Don't you know?
It's mostly because of that.
What?
They saw it.
Saw what?
The Lost Chamber.
You idiot! Don't even joke about it!
I think we're safe now.
Thanks.
Egghead is in the New World.
We're heading in the opposite direction.
Then I guess this is where we say goodbye.
Be careful.
Yeah.
I wish you luck.
This feels weird.
It wouldn't be so strange
if you were a pirate,
but a Revolutionary being so kind to me...
We both want to save the same person.
Yeah. Take care of my father!
Don't you know?
It's mostly because of that.
The Lost Chamber...
What would you like to ask us?
King Cobra of the Kingdom of Alabasta.
Well...
Where should I begin?
The World Government was founded
by 20 monarchs...
800 years ago.
As the creators of the world,
they relocated their families
to Mary Geoise.
They eventually became known
as the Celestial Dragons,
and have been reigning over the world
for 800 years.
Inside, the 20 monarchs
treated each other equally,
and to avoid any of them
rising to become a dictator,
they intentionally installed
an empty throne,
and placed their weapons around it
as a symbol of the oath
that no one would sit there.
Meanwhile, in the 20 countries
that lost their royal families,
new monarchs were selected
and have been in place ever since.
Therefore, the names of the royal families
of the First Twenty...
have been removed
from their home countries.
But Alabasta was different.
Queen Lily of the Nefeltari Family
had her name remain in the First Twenty,
but she didn't become a Celestial Dragon
and went back to Alabasta,
so the Nefeltari Family still exists
in her country.
For that reason, to be exact, there are
only 19 weapons surrounding the throne.
That's true. But so what?
I've been reading all the old books
that remain in my country.
All we can know...
is the history written in the literature
after the Void Century.
But it wasn't there. Queen Lily's name!
She never made it back
to the Kingdom of Alabasta.
Her younger brother
ruled the country thereafter.
Could you tell me what you know?
Is that what you want to ask us?
About 800 years ago?
It's true that the monarch
of the Nefeltari Family alone
didn't live here,
But we thought she went back
to her country, too.
Why she did it and where she went...
Since that was a long time ago,
there is no way for us to know.
I'm sorry. We have no idea.
Then what is the D?
Why are you asking that?
Well, actually, a short letter
she left 800 years ago...
has been passed down
through our royal family for generations...
PANGAEA CASTLE
Please stop!
Please!
You're hurting me!
Somebody, please help!
I did-eh! Father-sama!
I didn't give up!
I caught a giant mermaid-eh!
Mm-hm, well done! Charlos!
Somebody, please help!
Oh no... My dear Princess Shirahoshi...
What should I feed you-eh?
I'll climb on you and go around the town
every day-eh!
Shirahoshi is mine-eh!
Get out of my way-eh!
This feels great-eh!
If you don't obey me,
I'll give you hell-eh!
I refuse!
Somebody, please!
Help me!
Oh no! My daddy and all our guards
are in the Council Tower...
Please! Somebody!
When it comes to this...
Please...
Run!
No!
Hey, you mermaid.
You just said "I refuse"!
You're rebellious-eh!
Asking for help is the height of rudeness!
We were turned down by her anyway!
Yeah! Who cares if she lives or dies!
Out of my way!
You guys are just like wakame seaweed,
easily swayed by others!
The Kingdom of Ryugu!
You better not rebel against them!
Your country will be destroyed!
Sorry! We dropped our guard, Shirahoshi!
Brothers!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Now that we're here, you're safe!
Let's go home!
We'll never come back to this place again!
Brother Fukaboshi...
You guys should go home now-eh.
I'll keep this mermaid as my pet-eh.
Damn you Celestial Dragon!
How dare you do that to our sister!
We'll make you pay!
Do it-eh!
Invincible Slave, Kuma!
Big Brother!
Shirahoshi!
Rebecca-sama!
I'll help you now!
Rebecca! It's that man again!
It's so aggravating! I won't forgive them!
Hey, Myosgard!
I can beat him up this time, right?!
Yeah!
I'll take full responsibility for it!
A former Warlord of the Sea,
Bartholomew Kuma!
Poor guy!
But it doesn't matter! Let's go!
Ryuboshi! Mamboshi!
Yeah!
You can kill them-eh, Kuma!
Even if they're a royal family,
we can buy our way out-eh!
Especially because they're Fish-Men!
Damn you!
Fukaboshi-dono!
Royal families must restrain themselves!
-Get out of my way!
-Leave it to them!
What's the difference
between them and us?! Myosgard!
Our sister is in trouble...
They can get away with it!
Because they're pirates
and not responsible for any country!
Myosgard!
How dare you punch me the other day!
Kuma! Kill Myosgard!
Tontatta Combat!
Hasshoken Secret Art! Drill Dragon!
Leo-sama! Sai-sama!
-Don't do it!
-He's a Celestial Dragon!
Tail Hammer!
Nail!
Charlos!
They're doomed!
He must be dead! This is murder!
The murder of a Celestial Dragon!
The Marine Admirals will come!
No, Kuma-chan!
You don't have to follow
anyone's orders anymore!
Let's go home together!
What?!
What is a Giant doing here?!
Morley!
Karasu!
I got the keys from Sabo!
-What is he?!
-An intruder?!
That's Morley!
A captain of the Revolutionary Army!
Okay! I'll go down!
Son!
Let me ask you one more time.
What is the D?
Leave. We have nothing more to say.
Imu-sama.
King Cobra is still here!
Did he say Imu?!
Lily...
How far I have run
Without knowing it, I counted scars
A treasure map in my head all along
Still looking for the future
The real promise
Lies much deeper in my heart
A dream
That no one can catch up with
That's all I hold on to
To you who smiles like the sun
I'll sing the same song as that day
This wish I don't want to forget
Even when I grow up
Until it reaches you
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith, one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
Today we'll introduce this one!
Shirahoshi!
Her father is King Neptune of
the Kingdom of Ryugu.
Her mother is Queen Otohime. And she is
a princess of the Kingdom of Ryugu.
She was born on April 4th
and likes sea grape pasta!
To avoid the pirate Vander Decken IX's
persistent proposals
and long-distance attacks,
she'd been holed up
in a tower for a long time.
After she met Luffy, she went outside
for the first time in a while.
But Decken threw
an extremely massive ship, Noah, at her.
To keep Noah away from her island,
she summoned the Neptunians to stop it.
After her ability to communicate
with the Neptunians was awakened,
she had to take on another name,
Poseidon, the Ancient Weapon.
Later, she gathered her courage
and traveled to the surface
to attend the Reverie.
Father-sama, I...
If possible, I want to live on land!
I just hope the kind-hearted Shirahoshi
won't be used as an Ancient Weapon.
That's it for today!
Now that you've seen it,
donate to our research fund!
See you next time!
Surprised by the presence
sitting on the Empty Throne,
King Cobra prepares for death
as he learns the truth of the world.
Facing a cruel fate that he can't defy,
he entrusts Sabo
with the 800-year-old secret
of the Nefeltari Family!
On the next episode of ONE PIECE!
"The Entrusted Message!
King Cobra's Resolve"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!