(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
We all have different places we want to go
But first, we need
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
Sparks fly, no limit
This is where it starts
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
Are your dreams still pure?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
Still, all of us
In the middle of an adventure
All of us, I tell you travelers
No such thing as a pointless fight
When random contexts
Start to make sense on their own
The threads of time are spun back together
The world keeps changing along with us
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
"The Entrusted Message!
King Cobra's Resolve"
No one is supposed to sit there.
No one is allowed to run the world
at their sole discretion!
There are two things
that I want to tell you...
and one thing to ask you, Cobra.
Who are you?!
The name Imu sounds familiar.
It must be a coincidence,
but among the First Twenty...
Don't be nosy...
I won't answer...
But I'll tell you what you want to know.
"D" is...
the name of the people
who once opposed us.
It has appeared
in various places in recent years...
in hollow shells who don't even know
the meaning of their own name.
But like everything else,
it stems from
Queen Lily's blunder 800 years ago...
Blunder?!
Same with the scholars
who sniff around the 100-Year Void.
And the pirates who seek
the Ponegliffs to hunt treasure.
If it weren't for Lily's mistake
on that day,
the loathsome artifacts
called the Ponegliffs
would not be scattered all over the world.
One damning hypothesis...
can be made about this past event.
Were the Ponegliffs unleashed
really by mistake?
Or was it planned?
The answer to that...
must be written in Lily's letter
that arrived in Alabasta.
Why have you...
been referring to her only as
Queen Lily of the Nefeltari Family...
all this time?
Say the full name on the letter
that the queen sent.
This is it.
I don't think
I will be leaving this room alive.
If I lie,
is there any chance you'll let me go?
The moment you saw Imu-sama,
your fate was sealed.
He's right...
It's the biggest taboo in the world...
What's this situation?
It's obviously not normal.
This is how it was signed.
The queen ruling the Kingdom of Alabasta
800 years ago was...
Nefeltari...
D. Lily.
"D"...
Fire Fist!
Rook Check!
Where did you come from?!
I was hoping
I'd be able to take you all down,
but I never expected to find hell
at the top of the world
How annoying!
You're... Luffy-kun's...
brother, right?
You're a Revolutionary
but you're helping me?
Our enemies are
the ones who sit above the kings...
It's them.
How do you know Luffy?
He saved my life.
That's so Luffy.
Hold yourself together!
I'll get you out of...
Without me, you can make it.
It's too late for me. Leave me behind!
I'll save you!
There is something I discovered.
I don't want you to die here!
I need you to tell Luffy-kun and Vivi...
Luffy and Princess Vivi?!
Tell them that we share the moniker "D"!
What?
Is it a coincidence?
Is what a coincidence?
You both...
They're cooked!
Looks delicious!
Hey! You can't take two at once!
I'm hungry!
But you can't...
Yummy!
Gee, man...
Yeah, it's good!
Sabo.
You were just about to say something.
Yeah.
I wonder if it's a coincidence
that you both have "D" in your name.
"D"?
Monkey D. Luffy and Portgas D. Ace.
There's "D" in both.
Oh, yeah.
I don't give a damn about names.
Do you want a "D" initial, Sabo?
What?!
-Sa-D-Bo!
-Don't put it there!
I can put it wherever I like!
Sa-D-Bo! Sa-D-Bo!
I finally see the path Alabasta must take...
Stay with me, King Cobra!
Hold yourself together!
King Cobra!
"The Ponegliffs..."
"Bear the flag of the dawn..."
"Nefeltari D. Lily."
I'm counting on you!
I'm counting on you, Sabo-kun!
King Cobra!
Live on!
Oh, no!
Who's there?
H-He got killed!
Cobra is dead!
I never liked him,
but I'm not vile enough to celebrate!
I witnessed something terrible!
I came to know
the dark side of the World Government!
I didn't want to!
Who was that?!
I'm screwed!
Who are you?!
King Wapol!
Is there something wrong?
I... didn't see anything!
I don't know anything!
The council has already started
in the round table chamber.
Let us walk you there.
N-No! I don't wanna stay here!
Wait!
King Wapol!
W-What's wrong with him?
GRAND COUNCIL ROUND TABLE CHAMBER
King Cobra and King Wapol
are not here yet...
We just received word. Both of them
wanted you to carry on without them...
I guess King Cobra used up all his energy
with his impassioned speech.
He's clearly satisfied now
that the Seven Warlords' matter is closed.
That must be it!
Okay, let's take care of
the remaining agenda items.
First, the Four-Nation Alliance
in the North Blue
is calling for independence...
Moonfish mambo! Shake, shake!
Cheer up, Shirahoshi.
Dancing will make you feel better!
Thank you.
Shirahoshi.
The council will eventually be over.
Let's wait at the Red Port
where those idiots won't come.
Okay.
What's wrong?
I want to speak with Vivi-sama.
I wonder where she went...
Why are you doing this?! Untie me!
Who ordered this? I'll tell the world
everything that happened here!
Whoa-whoa, you're too honest.
No one would want to set you free
after hearing that.
You really are a feisty woman!
JABRA, CIPHER POL "AIGIS" ZERO
I'm sorry...
but no one will help you, Princess.
You'll just be reported as missing
and kept as a pet by someone.
KALIFA, CIPHER POL "AIGIS" ZERO
Nothing is certain in life!
Now you feel the pathos of living!
KUMADORI, CIPHER POL "AIGIS" ZERO
Hey, you just looked at Kumadori's cards.
BLUENO, CIPHER POL "AIGIS" ZERO
I wouldn't go that far to win.
Come clean.
A pair of sixes.
FUKUROU, CIPHER POL "AIGIS" ZERO
Is Shirahoshi okay?
What?! You're worried about someone else
in this situation?
Looks like there was
another incident earlier,
but, well, as it turns out, she's fine.
Good...
Those who beat up the Celestial Dragon
that tried to kidnap the mermaid...
We're Straw Hat Luffy's subordinates!
We're not afraid of the Celestial Dragons!
They proudly declared themselves winners
and threw the plaza into turmoil.
On top of that, in the Land of the Gods,
Fujitora helped the Revolutionaries
free the slaves,
so Ryokugyu got pissed
and they got into a big fight...
Hey, Fujitora!
Do you know what you're doing?!
Did you forget?
I told you what I wanted to destroy
was the system.
You're the one who forgot something!
We're the Navy!
Nothing more, nothing less!
I don't want to lie.
Okay, okay,
so you're not gonna give an inch...
Cut the crap, Fujitora!
I'm not gonna forgive you!
Jeez...
I don't want them to give us
any more trouble.
This Reverie is a mess.
Well, that's none of your business,
Princess.
Why don't you worry about yourself?
I have to do something
or I'll be kept as a pet, too?
Give me a break!
What's that?
Someone's...
Help me! I didn't see anything!
Wapol?!
Get out of my way!
Oh!
Move out of my way!
I don't wanna...
get caught!
What was that about?
That was King Wapol, right?
Oh, damn!
Vivi's gone!
What?!
No!
What happened?!
Don't tell me...
She escaped!
Thanks, Wapol!
Vivi! When did you get here?!
You helped me escape!
You idiot! Get out of there!
Why are you in such a hurry?
Don't ask!
You're even shedding tears!
Hey!
How do you do? Kinderella-sama.
Have you seen my husband?
No, I have not seen him...
...Oh!
...King Wapol!
Darling, I've been looking for you!
Where have you been?!
Who is that young woman?!
Hey, Wapol! How far are you gonna go?!
I'm gonna go as far as I can!
To the end of the world
where no one'll follow me!
I'll come with you! Take me!
Is he eloping with her?!
How far I have run
Without knowing it, I counted scars
A treasure map in my head all along
Still looking for the future
The real promise
Lies much deeper in my heart
A dream
That no one can catch up with
That's all I hold on to
To you who smiles like the sun
I'll sing the same song as that day
This wish I don't want to forget
Even when I grow up
Until it reaches you
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith, one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
Today we'll introduce this one!
Nefeltari Cobra!
He was the 12th king of the Kingdom
of Alabasta and Vivi's father!
He was born on February 13th
and liked a dessert called knafeh!
He was a great ruler who believed that
"a country is its people."
Even when he was suspected of stealing
rain through Crocodile's trickery,
he didn't try to crush
the rebels by force.
When blackmailed into giving up
the location of the Ancient Weapon Pluton,
Cobra tried to sacrifice himself
to kill Crocodile.
But he was saved
by Luffy's heroic actions.
Overcome this war and survive!
Kingdom of Alabasta!
Later, Cobra attended the Reverie,
and after a heated debate,
he won the approval of many monarchs...
to pass the abolition of
the Seven Warlords system!
He was a great king,
both stern yet playful!
With this decision,
the world began to move even faster!
That's it for today!
Now that you've seen it,
donate to our research fund!
See you next time!
Vivi and Wapol attempt to flee
the turbulent Holy Land Mary Geoise.
Sabo heads for the Kingdom of Lulusia
with King Cobra's words in his heart.
And as if to corner them,
the Five Elders' attack finally begins!
On the next episode of ONE PIECE!
"The World Is Shaken! The Ruler's Judgment
and the Five Elders' Actions!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!