["Baby Got Back" playing through headset]
[electronic chiming]
[music stops]
[chiming continues]
Fine.
Huh.
[grunts]
What the hell?
[beeping]
[breathing heavily]
[breathes shakily] Hi.
Uh, it's Barnes.
I'm... I'm getting a really weird
reading out here and...
Barnes.
Outpost 47. Yeah.
I need to speak to
Assistant Director Verdugo...
Yeah. I'll hold.
- [breathes shakily]
- [beeping continues]
[growling]
Du-Ho.
- [Lee] Down!
- [Cate grunts]
Kentaro!
Kentaro, run!
- Come on. Move on.
- Run!
Let's go. Come on.
[roars]
[in Japanese] Shit.
[growling]
[both grunting]
- [in English] Nice shooting, Tex.
- At least I tried.
- You could've gotten killed, you idiot.
- Quiet.
[footsteps thudding]
[creature growling]
- [thudding continues]
- [rumbling]
[growling continues]
[May groaning, shivers]
[gasps, groans]
[creature growls]
[May whimpering]
[breathing shakily, groaning]
[footsteps departing]
- [Kentaro whispering] What do we do now?
- [breathes shakily]
We can't fight it.
I wouldn't recommend it.
I think we're in the clear for the moment.
[May gasps, groans]
- Goddamn it! Son of a bitch!
- No, no, no, no, no. [shushes]
[panting] My legs are soaking wet.
[shushes] Then we gotta move quick.
[May whimpers]
[Kentaro] Come on, May.
Get up. Get up, get up.
- Come on. May, you good?
- [groaning]
[May] Am I good?
I'm gonna die of hypothermia.
Are you happy we came?
[breathing heavily]
[person, in Japanese]
Your work is a bold statement.
Why this?
Why now?
Uh...
[person] House lights!
You hesitated.
It's a complicated question.
And you've had months to
come up with an answer.
Art...
...comes from a place you don't
feel comfortable talking about.
To me it's just intuitive.
I respect your process.
But if buyers are going
to plunk down money, good money,
they want to know what they are getting.
Who they are getting.
People...
...don't buy the art...
they buy the artist.
I know, Kimi.
I'm sorry.
You have two hours before
we open the doors
to figure out an answer
that makes me believe you.
We both have a lot at stake tonight.
[Kimi, speaking Japanese]
[Kentaro] Hey, Mom.
"Kentaro Randa's assertive
exploration of parallels and interiors
invites the viewer to challenge
their assumptions about identity."
Who knew my son was so provocative?
I'm not.
Everyone's going to love it.
It wouldn't be very "provocative"
if everyone loved it.
[sighs]
Hey...
...I'm proud of you.
So is your father.
He hasn't even seen it.
He will tonight.
He's coming straight from the airport.
[chuckles]
I'm going to get some air...
...before everyone wants to meet
the "provocative" new artist.
Kentaro...
...you've worked hard for this.
You deserve it.
There are snacks.
[Emiko, in English] Mmm.
[in Japanese]
Did you just take my picture?
No.
[in English] Bullshit.
[in Japanese] I saw you.
[Kentaro] I was taking a picture
of my poster for my show,
and you walked in front of it
gawking like a tourist.
[in English] "Parallels and Interiors."
Sounds pretentious.
Incredibly.
You know what would be
incredibly respectful is if you...
Yeah.
- Deleted.
- Thank you.
Is there a reason you don't like
your picture being taken?
I...
It's a very nice picture.
Are you hitting on me?
Just being honest.
Is this really you?
Yeah.
Is there wine?
It's cheap. Bad. Pretentious.
[chuckles]
Pretentious wine.
Right.
Do you like whiskey?
I like expensive whiskey.
You're in luck. Japan has
some very expensive whiskey.
Cool.
- I know a place.
- Now?
But don't you have a show?
Um, I'll make an entrance later.
Oh.
[chuckles] Okay.
I'm Kentaro.
I'm May.
May.
[Kentaro] May. May.
Where are you going? Slow down.
Slow down? [pants]
Unless you want to add a set of toes
to what you already owe me,
you need to speed your ass up.
He's right, May. Conserve your energy.
Wet legs,
you're gonna be fighting hypothermia.
[Kentaro] We gotta get you dry.
No. Even if there was anything out here
to build a fire with,
we can't sit still
with that Titan on the prowl.
- You still think it's out there?
- [Lee] Hell if I know.
[May] What are you ta... What happened to
your centuries of experience now, huh?
It's a Titan, May.
They're like snowflakes.
Never came across two that were same.
Okay. Well, maybe there's some info
on these precious files of yours.
Go to hell
- and take your life's work with you.
- Hey. Easy with these. Now come on, May.
[Cate] Once the sun goes down,
the temperature's gonna drop
by the minute.
We've got no food, no shelter.
No Du-Ho.
[sighs] Where the hell are we going?
Northwest. We head for the coast.
Greater probability
of running into people there.
[sighs]
- I think I saw something from the plane.
- [Lee] What?
[stammers] Saw what?
Some kind of structure.
Looked like a big golf ball.
[Lee scoffs]
It had to be man-made,
like a building or settlement.
All right. All right.
Did either one of you see it?
No.
But May did.
What? No.
No. You said you saw something.
I didn't see anything.
[in Japanese] You're taking their side?
[in English] Is it 'cause
you're pissed at me?
No. This has nothing to do with you.
This is about me freezing to death.
I'm trying to save you. Will you just...
Trust me.
- [knocks]
- [Kentaro, in Japanese] Sota?
[Sota] Password.
Sota. It's me, man. Kentaro.
[Sota] Who?
Kentaro.
- [Sota] Password.
- [static]
[in English] Okay. Forget about it.
This place is a dump.
[in Japanese] Dump!
[Sota] Hurry up!
[door buzzing]
Dump?!
She didn't mean it.
[chuckles] Prove me wrong.
[chuckles]
[in English] I like you.
[in Japanese]
And you're too easy to mess with.
[in English] Okay. You've proved me wrong.
[in Japanese] May, this is Sota.
Owner.
Manager.
Asshole.
[chuckles] Guilty of all charges.
[in English] Wait.
You have your own bottle?
You are as pretentious as I thought.
That's how it works here.
Uh-huh.
- [in Japanese] But maybe we can do better.
- [Sota, in English] Okay.
Oh. Okay.
So, you're a successful artist.
I designed the lighting here.
[glasses clinking]
- What? No way.
- Yeah.
Oh.
So, he lets me pretend,
and even open early for me.
[speaks Japanese]
What do you do?
Uh, computer shit.
It's not nearly as interesting as art.
How long have you been doing it?
Since I was little.
But as a job, I guess, since tonight.
What? Like... What do you mean? [chuckles]
- Like, tonight's your first show?
- Yeah.
Don't you feel like you should be there?
Um, I'm letting the suspense build.
- It's all part of the act.
- Oh. Part of the act.
Is this part of the act?
W-What do you mean?
The secret whiskey bar and you,
the artist, next big thing.
[in Japanese] Does he bring other girls?
As a bartender, I can't say.
- [chuckles]
- [chuckles] Asshole.
[in English] I mean,
I didn't say it was a bad act.
I mean, as far as acts go.
This isn't an act.
I judge an artist based on their art,
not on a suit and a haircut.
- [lock clicking]
- [keys jingle]
[door closes]
What?
Why isn't this stuff in the gallery?
[Kentaro] These aren't for sale.
[May sighs]
You're definitely
more than just a haircut.
Kimi sent me to her stylist.
People buy the artist.
I mean, sure.
Rich pricks who have
more money than good taste.
Why don't you tell Kimi
what pieces you want in the show?
[Kentaro] Hmm.
It's her gallery.
- She was taking a chance on me...
- Chance on you?
Like, out of the goodness of her heart?
Come on. That's bullshit.
People don't give other people a shot
unless there's something in it for them.
That's pretty cynical.
That's life.
[cell phone chimes]
You should probably go.
The, um... The rich pricks are waiting.
Come with me.
Not really my crowd.
Mine either.
[chuckles] Get used to it, hotshot.
Wait. [grunts]
Okay.
Now you can go.
- [scoffs]
- [chuckles]
[Cate sighs] Okay.
Somebody has to say it.
I don't see any buildings.
It must be behind those hills.
[sighs] Must it?
- Kentaro, we agreed...
- You all agreed.
[Lee] You got passion, kid.
I'll give you that.
- Stop treating me like a kid.
- [Cate stammers] Hold on.
I know what I saw.
- [Cate] No, no, no.
- [Lee] What?
Over there.
- [Lee] What? Where?
- [Cate] Right there. What is that?
[Lee] Oh, yeah. I see it.
I don't know. Lights on an oil rig maybe,
or a local settlement.
[Cate] Point is, it's out there, right?
- We follow something we can all see.
- Yeah.
You don't know how far that is.
That Titan can catch you
before you get halfway there.
Whatever I saw is closer.
- Yeah, if it exists.
- [May] Okay. Kentaro.
Look, you have a brilliant imagination,
but now is not the time to use it.
I'm going.
Alone if I have to.
Oh, my God. You obstinate asshole.
- So, what? You wanna die to prove a point?
- Do you?
- No.
- [Lee] Stop. Stop. Please, stop.
You think you saw something?
Yeah. I know what I saw.
Then go, and don't stop until you find it,
and then get help.
We'll do the same.
Good luck.
We're all gonna need it.
No. No. We can't just let him leave.
He's made his choice, Cate. Let's go.
[Verdugo] Dr. Barnes, I understand
you have something for us?
[Barnes] Yeah. Hold on.
Sharing my screen now.
- What are we looking at here?
- Radiation.
Specifically, gamma rays
in the 30 exahertz range.
- Where is this radiation coming from?
- That's the crazy thing.
You only see these kinds
of spikes from pulsars.
Supermassive black holes from outer space.
- But not this?
- No.
This was coming from the earth.
Where exactly on the earth?
Well, the detector that picked it up
is an old model,
it's pretty much an antique.
- They're pretty finicky.
- I'll note it in the next budget request.
- Where?
- It was a rhythmic pulse,
well, like... like a pulsar
but as far as I know,
there aren't any pulsars in Alaska.
Thank you, Dr. Barnes.
Send us everything you have
and we'll get an analysis team
out to you right away.
Wait, wait, wait!
That's not the big thing.
The last time anyone
saw readings like this
was right before the last emergence event.
From Janjira and Yucca Flats.
Before G-Day.
[breathing heavily]
[May, echoing] Kentaro!
[Kentaro] May?
Is that you?
[Cate, echoing] Kentaro!
Cate?
Shaw?
[voices whispering]
[Cate] We shouldn't have let Kentaro go.
[grunts] He won't survive the night.
[sighs]
He just needs to hang on
until we get help.
[grunts, breathing heavily]
- Come on, May, let me carry that bag.
- No. Stop. No!
He wants something.
She's getting delirious.
Few more steps, okay?
Think of how warm it'll be
when we get there.
Blankets, hot coffee.
- Whiskey.
- [chuckles]
[breathing heavily] Come on.
[grunts]
No.
[all grunting]
[breathing heavily, groans] Shit.
[Cate] What? We're back at Dad's tent?
- How did this happen?
- [sighs]
[Cate] We're walking in circles.
Uh, Titans have odd effects
on their surroundings
and how we experience them.
The cloud we flew through, this place,
it's stranger than you think.
It's stranger than anybody knows.
[shivering]
If we don't warm her up, she's gonna die.
We can all die if that Titan's still here.
Well, I'm not leaving here without her.
We are not losing another person.
Beautiful.
It is.
Tell me why you don't wanna go
to your gallery opening again.
Why does it matter to you if I go?
Well, it doesn't.
But I don't think you should be ashamed
to take credit for what you do.
What do you do?
I just brought you here
and bared my artist's soul.
You haven't told me shit about yourself.
I told you. I do computer shit.
- Computer shit?
- Yeah.
Yeah, okay. Come on.
I'm from Tacoma. Tacoma sucks.
So, I came to Japan.
Japan is cool.
Is that better?
[Kentaro muttering] I'm sorry.
It's okay. You didn't make Tacoma suck.
So, you can stay as long as you want,
or you can come with me?
This is your party. [sighs]
I've already seen all the best stuff.
Can I see you again?
- Give me your number. [chuckles]
- This is your phone?
Yeah. I like a physical button.
- [cell phone ringing]
- [Kentaro] Um, you need to...
Ignore it.
[buttons beeping]
Try not to break anything.
[chuckles] How would you tell?
[cell phone ringing]
Hello? Hey.
[sighs] I'm traveling.
For work, yeah.
No. Look, you... you gotta stop calling me.
I... [sighs] I'll call you
when I'm back, yeah?
Okay, you too.
Yeah, bye.
Beautiful.
Beautiful. [shivering]
- This shit is so beautiful.
- [Cate] May.
Stay with me. May. May.
Oh... [stammers] My legs are burning.
Like pins and needles?
More like swords and daggers.
- [groans]
- That's really good.
Your nerves are waking up.
You don't have frostbite yet.
[May breathes shakily] Yet.
Good bedside manner.
[shivering]
Hey. If anything happens to me,
just get in touch with my sister.
Her name's... [inhales sharply]
Her name is Lyra.
No. Let's not go there.
She's the only...
only person that I can call.
I'm gonna... I'm gonna give you her number.
I'm sure Kentaro knows h...
No. He doesn't know shit.
[Lee] Hope you're not talking about me.
[sighs] Compliments of Du-Ho.
Crackers and chocolate.
How's she doing?
[breathes shakily] Better.
[exhales sharply]
[Lee] All right. Her pants are dry.
[groans] We're gonna
have to stoke that fire.
[grunts]
This is nothing but kindling.
I mean, it's not gonna last very long.
And who knows what's in your dad's papers.
I mean, it could tell us
what he was doing here.
Theories, discoveries, where he went.
[shivering]
Let it burn.
[breathing deeply]
[rumbling]
Get your gear on! We gotta move! Come on!
Get back to where we hid before.
- Come on.
- May!
- [whimpers]
- Go, go, go, go, go!
- [whimpers] May.
- [Lee] Wait, wait. Stop. Don't move.
[Cate] It could be anywhere. Listen.
[shrieks, gasps]
[creature roars]
I can't run from that thing anymore.
We may not have to.
This morning,
Outpost 47 registered readings
I consider noteworthy.
Dr. Barnes.
- [tech 1] Oh, my God.
- [tech 2] What?
That can't be right.
These readings mirror, uh...
The gamma-ray flare
before the San Francisco...
event.
Call it what it was. An attack.
Well, what do you suggest?
Full mobilization?
- Try out your Titan warning system?
- [Tim] Uh, excuse me. [clears throat]
- [Bagheri] Create a worldwide panic?
- Better than a thousand dead.
- Or 10,000.
- Excuse me.
[Bagheri] We don't know if these creatures
have malevolent intent.
- [Tim] Excuse me!
- Quiet down.
[shushes] Tim, you have something?
We can't dismiss Bill Randa's files.
Now, look, Lee Shaw was there.
He knows something that we don't.
- That's why he's going after the files.
- Quiet!
Uh, most of you all don't know me,
and if you do,
I'm the troll from the basement
that you try to avoid in the break room.
It's fine. It's not like I work here
for the after-work karaoke anyway.
Your point.
[sighs] I thought that we were here
to learn everything we can
in any way that we can
so no one else has to lose
another loved one in a Titan event.
And I would've thought
that a bunch of people
who signed up to study
giant, atomic-powered monsters
would be a little bit more
open-minded about it.
[Lee] We may be knocked on our asses
but we're not done yet,
'cause now we know how our enemy works.
- We do?
- [Shaw groans] Yeah.
That Titan didn't go after us,
it went after the fire.
Didn't go after Kentaro, it went after
that burning airplane engine.
That's how it's tracking us.
It's drawn to the heat. Oh, my God.
Then why did it toss that airplane
like a chew toy... [pants]
...and come chasing after us?
Because my brother tried saving our asses
by shooting a flare at it.
And after the flare,
we were the warmest things.
And this is how we beat this damn thing.
We dangle the biggest, brightest,
hottest object we can in front of it.
Never been so thankful for a full bladder.
Aviation fuel.
Flint.
Gonna light this thing brighter
than Times Square on VJ Day.
Uh, what? What day?
We build a bonfire. We feed it.
And then while that Titan's
absorbing its heat...
[grunts] ...we hightail it to the coast.
I'll carry you if I have to.
[grunting]
May, just a little further, okay?
We're gonna make it.
I'm not.
Sooner or later
you're gonna have to ditch me, okay?
Yes. And if the time comes,
you ditch him too.
Save yourself, Cate.
One of us
has to make it out of here alive.
[voice, echoing] Who's there?
Hello?
- Hello?
- [voice, echoing] What are you doing here?
Are you real?
[voice, echoing] I thought I was alone.
So did I.
[voice, echoing] You shouldn't be here.
[in Japanese] Dad...
Don't leave me!
Wait, Dad!
It's me!
Don't...
[wheezing, coughing]
[breathes shakily]
[scratching]
[gasps]
I did sell a few pieces...
...but Kimi dropped me anyway.
[scratching]
"It's a huge opportunity," you said.
"You're so talented."
"You can do this."
"I believe in you."
That's what you said that time.
How the hell...
...would you know
if I was ready or not?
But I didn't want to disappoint you.
So I couldn't face you...
How was I supposed to know
I'd never see you again?
Dad?
I wouldn't have missed this for anything.
Everybody loved it.
Your mother loved it.
[distorted] I loved it too.
I'm proud of you.
Congratulations.
[distorted dialogue]
[static]
[static continues]
[Cate, in English]
Are we really doing this?
[Lee] It's a funeral pyre, Cate.
Du-Ho always wanted to go out
in a blaze of glory.
I'm just pouring one out for the guy
who loved getting one over on me.
First night we met, brother,
I... I couldn't believe
how you were drinking me
underneath the table that night.
- [helicopter whirring]
- [Lee] And then I realized
- every time you took a shot...
- Do you hear that?
- Shaw. Shaw! It's...
- ...all you really...
[roars]
[both screaming]
- Go! Run!
- May!
Hey, big boy! Big boy! Over here!
Oh, Jesus. No. Where is it? No.
- Help! Help! Help!
- [grunting]
- [whimpering]
- [growling]
[screaming]
[groans] Need a shield
to ride a rocket ship.
Dinner time, you son of a bitch. [grunts]
[grunts]
[screaming]
May, come on.
You can do this.
The chopper! Let's go.
[grunting]
[footsteps thudding]
[roars]
- [Cate grunting] May! Come on!
- [May] Oh, shit.
[Cate] I got you!
- Come on, hurry!
- [Cate] Kentaro!
- Let's go!
- Kentaro?
- [Kentaro] Come on. Go.
- [Lee] Go. Go.
[Lee] Pick it up!
[Cate shrieks]
[grunts]
They said the signal was so weak,
they almost didn't hear me
on the emergency channel.
I never thought I'd thank someone
for abandoning their family,
but here we are.
Dad was there. Before me.
- Just like at his camp.
- How do you...
Someone had to fix the radio that I found.
Left a mess of shavings behind.
He made it out.
He's alive.
[May] Thank you.
[radio chatter]
No. No, no, no. Oh, goddamn it.
Damn it.
[Tim] Colonel Shaw!
It's an honor to finally meet you!