[tense music]
[narrator] What is a Pharaoh?
She is the sands and the sky.
♪ See the sky ♪
And everything in between.
♪ Catch the dream ♪
Egypt is her firstborn.
♪ Standing tall until the end ♪
And when the moment comes…
♪ I'll survive ♪
♪ I'm not falling down ♪
…she must be ready to sacrifice everything
to protect what she loves most.
[Mark Antony] What have you done?
["Love and Rage" playing]
[Cleopatra] I did what I had to do
to protect what is mine.
[Thyrsus] My lord, Octavian,
he's willing to grant your request.
On one condition.
Kill Antony.
[Mark Antony] All I want is your trust.
[theme music]
[upbeat music]
[children laughing]
[laughing continues]
[Shelley] After the Battle of Actium,
Mark Antony enters a period
of clinical depression.
[Jacquelyn] Their navy is gone.
Their military is splintered.
[Shelley] He does not speak to Cleopatra.
And her confidence in him is eroded.
And so, confidence
in their relationship is eroded.
[Shelley] "Can I trust him?"
"Does he trust me?"
[Shelley] There's a lot of doubt there.
[Jacquelyn] Cleopatra knew
the full might of Rome
coming against Egypt
spelled the end for an independent Egypt.
[Jacquelyn]
There is no question that they are
in immediate jeopardy.
[Jacquelyn] Cleopatra knows
that in order to protect the continuance
of Egypt as a dynastic state,
that she needs to protect her heirs.
So, she sends them away
to make sure that they are safe.
[Shelley] If her children don't survive,
particularly Caesarion,
who was her co-pharaoh…
that's the end.
[Cleopatra crying]
[Colleen] As the earthly incarnation
of the goddess Isis,
Cleopatra is also the earthly embodiment
of divine motherhood.
[Colleen] Just think about
how heart-wrenching it must have been
to send her children away.
And yet, she had no choice politically
or for their safety.
[Charmion] Pharaoh, we have to go.
I know, just give me a minute.
[Cleopatra cries]
You two…
[soft chuckle]
You two are one blood, hm?
[Cleopatra] My blood.
Divine blood.
Don't you forget that.
[Selene] I won't forget.
[Charmion] Pharaoh.
[Cleopatra crying]
The things that are most precious
to Cleopatra are her children.
Because as long as they're safe,
as long as they're alive…
she's alive.
And there's hope for Egypt.
Cleopatra is always a diplomat first
and a military strategist second.
[Shelley] It's clear now
that diplomacy isn't gonna work.
Cleopatra doesn't want war.
She doesn't feel
that Mark Antony is ready for war.
Kill Antony.
His life for yours.
[Thyrsus] And your children's, of course.
[Sally-Ann] I think Cleopatra would
consider killing Mark Antony.
He is no longer any use to her.
And has, quite frankly,
become a liability at this point.
She might believe
that she still has a chance
of coming to terms with Octavian.
Perhaps, even by betraying Mark Antony.
Because, after all, Mark Antony
was Octavian's primary enemy.
There's really no reason that Cleopatra
cannot remain queen of Egypt
if Mark Antony is out of the picture.
Mark.
Thyrsus sent a message from Octavian.
He says he can guarantee safety
for the children and I…
[sighs deeply]
…if I kill you.
[scoffs]
So that's why you are here.
No.
I turned him down.
-We are in this together.
-[laughs]
Yeah.
Like we were together in Actium.
I sent our children away
because I choose us.
I know that together,
no one can defeat us.
Rome and Egypt.
Where is he?
[Shelley] Those of us who are romantics,
we want this to be
the greatest love story of all time.
But Cleopatra was not a romantic.
She was a pragmatist.
Cleopatra is interested
in self-preservation, um,
of herself and also her children,
but her country, too.
[Shelley] And she believes, at this point,
that Mark Antony
is still the key to that partnership.
[tense music]
[grunts]
Tell Octavian we are done!
[Mark Antony pants]
[Sally-Ann] Mark Antony seems to be
a bit of a loose cannon.
He is now behaving irrationally,
he's taking it out on the messenger.
[panting]
[Shelley] If Cleopatra is going to retain
her place on the throne,
she has to have Rome as her partner.
Tell that coward,
if he wants me dead, do it himself.
[Sally-Ann] Mark Antony isn't going
to enter into any negotiations.
There's not gonna be
any other ending other than war.
[Debora] Octavian has declared war
on Cleopatra.
She understands
that neither she nor Mark Antony
were going to get away from this.
[rhythmic thumping]
[Islam] In the spring of 30 BC,
Octavian, as he enters Egypt,
sends a mammoth, uh, army.
It's, it's the biggest
army invasion in Roman history
until this point.
With the defections
from Cleopatra's forces to Octavian
and Mark Antony's losses
at the Battle of Actium,
Octavian's legions now heavily outnumber
those of Cleopatra and Antony.
Octavian wants to finish this
once and for all.
[insects chirping]
[Jacquelyn] Egypt is unusually wealthy
in terms of their material wealth.
[Colleen] Octavian needs this
to pay his troops.
[Jacquelyn]
Octavian wants to annex Egypt badly.
Rome will treat them as their breadbasket
and not care if they impoverish Egypt.
[tense music]
[Colleen] Octavian's army marches
towards Pelusium.
Octavian could have sailed
straight for Alexandria
but he does not.
He regroups and moves his forces by land.
[Colleen] This is important
because, along the way,
Octavian is securing
alliance after alliance.
[Islam] He is keen
to get the local population
against Mark Antony
and in turn, against Cleopatra.
[Debora] Octavian has released
this vicious propaganda against Cleopatra,
so even though Mark Antony was the one
who was unfaithful to his sister,
Cleopatra is framed
as this great seductress.
As a temptress, as a drunk, as a witch.
It's misogynistic and it's xenophobic.
So, she's a threat.
The Roman senators see this woman
influence two of its great heroes
and they've had enough.
It's about time,
as far as they're concerned,
for Octavian to put an end
to Cleopatra's meddling in Roman affairs.
That's the perfect strategy
to gain the allegiance
of any of Mark Antony's remaining allies.
[Colleen] Octavian is ensuring
that when it comes time
for the final battle
with Mark Antony and Cleopatra,
that he will have no enemies to his rear.
[insects chirping]
[Colleen] As Octavian's army
marches towards Alexandria,
Mark Antony is in a serious depression.
Cleopatra attempts to improve his mood
by throwing a lavish banquet.
-[indistinct chatter]
-[celebratory music playing]
[Jacquelyn] The reason that Cleopatra
throws the banquet
is part of the religious ideology
of this area.
Mark Antony, as the manifestation
of the god Dionysus,
is the god of revelry
and this banquet would have served
to support and reinvigorate
that religious message of him
as a legitimate eastern monarch.
[indistinct chatter]
[Islam] It's directly challenging Rome.
It's saying, "We are in power."
[Islam] It's a declaration
that she doesn't care what Rome thinks.
It's a dangerous call for war.
[whispering]
[Jacquelyn] As Octavian's army
approaches Alexandria,
Antony and Cleopatra's forces
at this point,
are disorganized, they're demoralized.
[indistinct chatter]
The Commander of Pelusium has surrendered.
And defected to Octavian.
[Shelley] Octavian is receiving defections
from the Egyptian side
and from other allies
that used to be with Egypt
and they're now going over to Rome.
That two-faced Pelusium commander
will never see his wife or daughter again.
Not in this lifetime.
It will take more than that
to stop Octavian now.
I know.
It will take the help of the gods.
Lucky for you, you have one right here.
[soft music]
Octavian is no match for us.
[thrilling music]
[Cleopatra] Friends.
Even in the best of times,
there are traitors amongst us.
We know that in our own land,
some have betrayed Egypt,
opening their gates to Octavian's forces.
No one betrays Egypt
and gets away with it.
Your enemies are our enemies.
To Mark Antony.
[cheers, applause]
[Sally-Ann] The Egyptian people
must have been extremely nervous
about the Roman Army marching upon them.
Because Rome up until this point,
they've been seen as a support
and now they've essentially
become an enemy.
[indistinct chatter]
[Islam] It's too late for Cleopatra
to get on Octavian's side.
She's in quite deep now with Mark Antony.
Are you asleep?
No.
[Sally-Ann] So, she really does have
everything to lose at this point.
It's not only her own life
and her position,
but it's her country.
-[Mark Antony] How long?
-We have time.
-And eyes?
-Our scouts have eyes on them.
Tell the cavalry we leave now.
[Cleopatra] Thank you, Maelius.
[tense music]
[inhales]
[Colleen] The one advantage
that Cleopatra has
is that she's defending
her home territory.
And she knows
from prior experience with Julius Caesar,
that the Egyptians are no lovers of Rome.
Egypt does not want to be
under Roman control or Roman occupation.
[Jacquelyn] Mark Antony
is an accomplished military mind.
That is a very serious
home-field advantage for them.
He and Octavian's forces
meet right outside of Alexandria.
-[soldiers yelling]
-Come on!
[Shelley] Mark Antony is a soldier.
He knows what goes into winning a battle.
[Shelley] He enjoys going into battle.
He enjoys fighting alongside of his men.
Antony and Cleopatra's forces have had
some time to rest and recuperate.
[Jacquelyn] Whereas, Octavian's forces
have been on the active march
and so, uh, Antony's forces
are at least fresh.
[tense music]
[Cleopatra] What's going on?
Is there water and provisions
for the wounded?
Yes, yes, it's done.
-And the armory, has it been checked?
-[Iras] As we speak.
[Colleen] Based on previous experience,
Cleopatra knows the vulnerability
of Alexandria's water sources.
[Colleen] She knows
that they can be poisoned.
I want two guards stationed at every well
and every water supply.
[soldiers yelling]
The other disadvantage
that Mark Antony and Cleopatra face
is simply the lack of supplies and force.
They do not have the troops,
and they no longer have the supply lines.
[Shelley] Cleopatra is a lover,
not a fighter.
She understands
that war can go either way,
she feels that Mark Antony
doesn't really understand
the lay of the land in Alexandria.
[grunts]
[Shelley] Maybe he has bit off
-more than he can chew here.
-[Mark Antony] Come on!
She's nervous.
[grunts]
[horse neighs]
[swords clinking]
[somber music]
We have won the battle, but…
[Cleopatra] But what?
They have more troops, Cleopatra.
I know.
We are not done yet.
Are we?
No.
We are not done yet.
Good.
[Shelley] He's really worried.
Which makes Cleopatra worried.
[soft chuckle]
But she sends him off to the next battle.
[somber music]
[soldiers clamoring]
[soldier yells]
There's this huge siege.
[tense music]
-[swords clinking]
-[grunting]
Mark Antony is getting desperate.
[Colleen]
He has his archers fire offers of gold
to any of Octavian's forces who defect.
He's having to break the siege.
[Colleen] Mark Antony makes a bold
and risky move against Octavian.
He launches a land
and naval attack simultaneously.
Their forces do meet
right outside of Alexandria
which is a deciding, significant battle.
[grunts]
[neighs]
[swords clinking]
[soft music]
General, the Egyptian naval fleet
has defected to Octavian.
No, that can't be true.
I'm afraid it is, General.
No. No, no, no, no. No.
At this point,
nothing is stopping Octavian
from landing in Alexandria.
[soldiers clamoring]
[loud banging]
What was that?
Go and check what is happening, please.
-Okay.
-Quickly.
[soldiers yelling]
[Shelley] Cleopatra was convinced
the gates around Alexandria
could not be breached.
They were well protected.
[all clamoring]
When Octavian and his troops
make that breach,
it is clear to Cleopatra,
the Egyptian troops have defected.
Which means the country
is in the hands of Octavian.
[melancholy music]
[Shelley] For most of us,
if we were in Cleopatra's situation,
um, the end is nigh.
I think we would have
a nervous breakdown, panic attack.
[yelps, chuckles]
[Charmion] Our defenses are down,
we have to go.
[Shelley] Cleopatra is probably feeling
defiant at this point.
If they are here, it means the general--
Quiet, Iras.
[Charmion] Pharaoh, we have to go now.
[Colleen] Now even if Cleopatra manages
to hold on to her throne
or successfully passes it on
to one of her children,
Egypt is going to be a province
of the Roman Empire.
-Pharaoh, we need to--
-I said be quiet!
[melancholy music]
This needs to get to Antony.
[Charmion] Pharaoh, we have to go now.
Her life's work, her legacy,
it's in danger, if not gone.
[insects chirping]
[tense music]
[Cleopatra] Hurry.
Hurry!
[Sally-Ann]
Cleopatra gathers all her wealth
in her mausoleum in her tomb.
This is one of her last bargaining chips.
Octavian needs this treasure
to pay his troops.
[Colleen] Cleopatra's tomb
is only partially finished.
She's barricaded inside.
I won't let Octavian capture me.
We're going to burn it all down.
That bastard touches nothing.
[Colleen] Cleopatra is threatening
to set her tomb on fire
and to go up in flames
with her entire treasure.
[Mark Antony] Cleopatra!
Did you hear that?
-[Cleopatra] Mark?
-They're coming. They're coming for us.
-[Mark Antony] Drop something now.
-[panting]
Get a rope, quick!
Hold on, my love!
[grunts]
[panting]
Pull!
[strained grunt]
[effort grunting]
[Cleopatra screams]
Mark Antony has to actually
be hauled up through a window.
Mark Antony has attempted
to commit suicide
after receiving a note from Cleopatra.
[Shelley] We don't know
what was in that note.
Shakespeare would have us believe
Cleopatra fabricated her own suicide
in the hopes that that would prompt
Mark Antony to commit suicide.
The bravest thing to do,
according to a Roman person,
is to commit suicide.
[Jacquelyn] And this is a way to maintain
your valor and your dignity
-even in the face of death.
-[crying]
Just stay.
[sniffles]
[crying]
Cleopatra…
Shh, shh…
[sniffles]
[whimpers]
[Shelley] He wants to die with Cleopatra.
[wailing]
And he dies in Cleopatra's arms.
[somber music]
Octavian, our astute politician,
who is also ruthless…
does not want Cleopatra dead
at the hands of the Romans
because she becomes a martyr.
And all those Egyptians
who have defected to Octavian
are gonna rise up in rebellion.
This is a Pharoah.
You do not kill…
a Pharaoh.
To get into her barricaded tomb,
Octavian's men break through the roof.
[distant clattering]
[Cleopatra] Light the torch.
[Roman commander]
You, put that fire out, come on!
Seize her!
[screaming]
I am mistress of the two lands.
Thea Neotera.
I'm a god.
Do not disrespect me.
I would die for Egypt.
What would you die for?
[Cleopatra] No.
[all whimpering]
No. No!
[attendants whimpering]
Stop!
No!
[Shelley]
The soldiers take her to the palace
where she used to receive ambassadors.
Octavian comes in.
They've never met before.
Looks like your African sorcery
failed you this time.
Pharaoh?
You know, your witchcraft
must be very strong
to turn two great sons of Rome
against their own
because the talk
of your beauty flatters you…
immensely.
What are you smiling about?
Witch!
You're a lot shorter
than I thought you'd be.
You know…
your children look just like you.
Especially your eldest.
They'll be a great comfort to you in Rome.
[Shelley] At this point,
Cleopatra believes
that her children are safe.
She has sent them away
with trusted members of her household.
And so, she believes
she has nothing to fear.
You should have just taken my offer
when you had the chance.
I'm going to enjoy
dragging you through the streets.
And those…
bastard half-breeds of yours.
They're gonna watch.
[Shelley] She realizes that Octavian
has captured her children.
And it always amazes me
that she doesn't crumple at that point.
Get her out of here now!
One of the most important things
that any, uh, Roman military leader can do
to gain the support and love
of the Roman people
is to have a remarkable celebration
of his military victory called a triumph.
[Colleen] To complete his victory,
Octavian needs
to bring Cleopatra back to Rome
to parade her in his triumph.
[melancholy music]
[melancholy music continues]
See that this gets to Octavian.
[Cleopatra] Trust me,
he's gonna want to read it.
Don't worry,
we'll all be here when you get back.
[Jacquelyn]
Cleopatra writes a letter to Octavian
requesting that she and Antony
be permitted to be buried together
and to allow her son to inherit Egypt.
[Jacquelyn] What we're seeing
is this last moment of Cleopatra
clinging to this overarching goal
throughout her entire life
of trying to make sure
that the Ptolemaic Dynasty
will not die out.
That Egypt does not become
a province of the Roman Empire.
[Cleopatra] We'll do it together.
It's the right thing to do.
Worthy of a God.
[Shelley] She has a plan.
Cleopatra always has a plan.
She's researched poisons
that won't be painful,
that won't distort her body.
She decides how she's going to die.
[somber music]
[Shelley] And she decides
with whom she is going to die.
It's not Octavian,
it's not the Roman Senate,
it's Cleopatra.
She is in control.
[somber music]
[somber music continues]
[birds squawking]
[light music]
[approaching footsteps]
[Colleen]
When Octavian receives that letter,
he knows Cleopatra
is not going to come back to Rome
and she has committed suicide.
[somber music]
[Jacquelyn] Being taken in a Roman triumph
would have been tremendously humiliating.
It's very unlikely that Cleopatra
would've been treated with velvet gloves.
Defeated enemies
are usually killed right afterwards.
So she knew that her death
was on the horizon anyway.
There was no way
Octavian could have allowed her to live.
[Colleen] Octavian knows it's over.
[Shelley] We do not know the method
with which Cleopatra committed suicide.
The one that every film producer loves
is that she died as the result
of the bite of the Egyptian cobra or asp.
[Colleen]
The cobra is a symbol of royalty.
So even if the asp
was not a part of her suicide,
it was a perfect symbol to represent
that she was leaving this world
as queen of Egypt.
[Jacquelyn] Cleopatra and Mark Antony,
their burials have never been found.
We don't know whether or not
she got her last request,
that they get buried together.
[Shelley] The quest of archaeologists
looking for Cleopatra's tomb…
futile.
[fire crackling]
[Shelley] Octavian is not going
to allow a tomb
with the remains
of Cleopatra and Mark Antony.
That would have become
a center point for rebellion.
[fire crackling]
It was not the Roman tradition
to entomb bodies.
They didn't mummify bodies, they cremated.
I think Cleopatra and Mark Antony
were cremated.
[somber music]
This is the true turning point in history.
[tense music]
Egypt totally loses its independence.
[indistinct chatter]
[Shelley] It's over.
It becomes a province of Rome.
Egypt's long history
as a great civilization ends.
[Jacquelyn] Egypt now becomes
the grain basket of Rome.
Rome would not have been able
to go on militarily
without being able to spend
vast amounts of Egyptian wealth.
[Jacquelyn] Rome tapped the bank of Egypt
and impoverished it.
It really ends Egypt as the dynastic land
that we think of today.
Cleopatra is the last pharaoh of Egypt.
[epic music]
[Debora] Shortly thereafter,
Octavian has the Senate
declare him Emperor.
The Emperor Augustus.
[Islam] He wanted to be ruler forever.
That was his idea
of what a dictator should be.
[Sally-Ann]
Ironically, like Cleopatra before,
Octavian is elevated as a living god.
[Debora] Cleopatra's death
was one of the… final phases
of what we consider to be ancient Egypt.
[Debora] We still have
Cleopatra's other three children.
[Shelley] The children
of Mark Antony and Cleopatra,
they'll represent a threat to Octavian.
♪ They will come for you and me… ♪
Alexander Helios and Cleopatra Selene
and little Ptolemy Philadelphus
are taken back to Rome.
♪ From my deepest scar ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh ♪
However, there is no way
that he could permit Caesarion to live.
[Shelley] Caesarion was raised
to be a Pharoah.
He could rise up,
he could say, "I am Caesar's son.
I should be ruling Rome."
He's just too big a threat to Octavian.
So he is executed.
He, he is killed.
[Debora] When Octavian takes
the children back to Rome,
he parades them
behind an effigy of Cleopatra
with a snake or an asp clasped to her arm.
He humiliates them publicly
by having them walk behind
this effigy of their mother
and weighing them down with gold chains.
The chains were supposedly so heavy
that they were stumbling
and they could barely walk.
[Debora] People actually felt sympathy
for the children,
but after that,
he sent them, surprisingly,
to live with his sister, Octavia,
who was Mark Antony's wife
when these children were conceived.
[Sally-Ann] So the long-suffering Octavia
brings up Mark Antony's children.
The two boys fall off
the historical radar,
but Cleopatra Selene
marries Juba of Mauretania.
So, Cleopatra Selene, ironically,
becomes another African queen.
Cleopatra Selene rules over
a sumptuous court
at the capital of Mauretania,
much like Alexandria.
[Colleen] Cleopatra Selene's court
is also filled
with literature and philosophy and art.
Selene, like her mother before her,
has constructed a tomb.
It's one of the most impressive
of the ancient world.
[Sally-Ann] We know from some
of the remains in her tomb
and from the sides of their palaces,
that she actually took Egyptian statues
to her palaces
to continue that connection
to her mother and her homeland.
[Debora] She has a son
who becomes her and her husband's heir.
[Shelley] She named that son, Ptolemy,
after Cleopatra's father.
That dynasty continues, though,
because her granddaughter
marries into the Roman Imperial family.
And so Cleopatra lives on.
[Shelley] Even in antiquity,
she lived on through her daughter
and she lived on through her grandson.
[epic music]
Cleopatra is significant
in that she is the last ruler
of an independent, powerful Egypt.
[Debora] We think about
female empowerment.
There is no Rome without Egypt.
This is a woman exercising power.
[Colleen] Cleopatra was trying
to save the country
that she loved from destruction.
[Cleopatra] I am Isis.
Queen of Kings!
I would die for Egypt.
[Cleopatra] What would you die for?
[Colleen] She has become an icon.
I resisted Cleopatra
for a really long time.
Uh, in my scholarly life.
I said, "I am not gonna study you.
I'm not gonna study you."
I would have this recurring dream
where there was this shadowy figure,
certainly an ancient person,
clearly a woman,
who would say to me,
"You have to tell my story."
"You have to do it."
I want people to know
the story of Cleopatra
because she was an African queen.
And that's a fact that's been buried,
it's been erased, it's been white-washed.
Generation after generation
are absolutely mesmerized by Cleopatra.
Her story resonates,
I think, with every woman.
[narrator] Cleopatra was one
of the most influential rulers
the world has ever known.
Her legacy as the most famous
of all African Queens is assured.
[Shelley] She will live on until…
there's no one else to tell her story.
[closing theme music]