Jimmy?
How's that sweeping going?
Goin' good, Pop!
Hi. How are you?
Hello, sir. I was wondering
if, maybe, you could help me?
Yeah?
Well, I drove
into the city this morning...
Usually, I take the train,
but I was just in
such a rush to get
some medicine for
my son, Freddie.
He has epilepsy.
He had an attack this morning,
but during his fit,
he knocked the bottle of
medicine out of my wife's hand.
It just...
Bam, one huge puddle.
That's terrible.
But long story short,
I drove into town,
I bought the new medicine with
every last nickel in my pocket,
and then my car died.
God, that's just...
I know. When it rains,
it pours, right?
I tried the ignition, just nothing.
Not firing.
Anyway,
now I've convinced myself
that Freddie is gonna have
another seizure
before I get back
with the medicine.
So, if you can help me,
I'd be so grateful...
Well, I can come out
and check your car for you.
Maybe it's just a spark plug.
I got a box of plugs
back in the stockroom.
Thanks, and I appreciate that,
but if you could possibly
just spare $5 instead?
I'd rather grab a cab than take
a chance with my old clunker.
Yeah. $5?
If you can spare it.
Yeah, okay. Sure.
Psst!
Dad. C'mere!
C'mere!
Dad, it's a rip-off!
Just like that
bum from last week.
Jimmy...
Every grifter in
town knows that
this is the spot to come
for an easy handout.
"Grifter"? Where in the world
did you learn that word?
Dad. His story is baloney. He
probably doesn't even have a son.
He's conning you.
Jimmy, what if you're wrong?
You know what?
I'm sorry to bother you folks.
I'm gonna get outta here...
I'm...
No, no, no.
Dad... No, no bother.
Come on, no. Here.
Here $10 for you.
Sir, you're...
That's... That is so generous.
Of course, and you know what? I'm
gonna go back in the stockroom,
I'm gonna find
those spark plugs,
and we will get your car
started for you, okay?
Come on, Jimmy,
just man the till, okay,
and I'll just be back in a jiff.
Okay?
How much for a carton of Kools?
4 bucks.
Yeah, gimme a carton.
Money first.
Gimme two cartons.
Gosh, those spark
plugs are back here somewhere.
Just gimme one
more minute, okay?
Come on.
There are wolves and sheep
in this world, kid.
Wolves and sheep. Figure out
which one you're gonna be.
Okay, I found the...
Did he leave?
Did he just leave?
Sir?
Don't let me interrupt.
Hey. Sorry. You ready?
Hey, come on,
let's get this over with.
Thank you for seeing us.
We don't wanna take up
too much of your time,
so I'll get right to it.
Um, I regret to inform you that
with the benefit of hindsight,
Mr. Ehrmantraut will be amending
his original statement a tad.
A tad? A wee bit.
He's decided that he can no
longer in good conscience
claim that the gun found at the
scene belonged to Tuco Salamanca.
- So, whose gun was it?
- Who's to say?
You know how many guns
there are in Albuquerque?
Somewhere between the number of
rattlesnakes and
grains of sand.
So, a lot.
Was it your gun,
Mr. Ehrmantraut?
No, he is not saying that.
Can we hear it
from Mr. Ehrmantraut?
The gun wasn't Salamanca's.
That's all I can tell you.
You told us it was.
You said Salamanca pulled it
and pointed it at you.
Well, he didn't.
Why are you
changing your story?
Good citizenship.
Look, there was only one set
of prints on the gun,
Salamanca's.
How's that gonna happen
if it wasn't his?
That's not really for my
client to say now, is it?
He's not a forensics expert.
Who knows? Maybe it fell
from a passing bird's beak.
And Mr. Salamanca caught it
and tried to throw it away.
I mean, the possibilities
are endless.
Has Salamanca threatened you,
Mr. Ehrmantraut?
Hey.
We wanna put this
guy away for years.
The gun makes all the
difference, you know that.
You gonna let this person
victimize you twice?
Forget about the gun.
All right?
The gun was not Salamanca's.
If you try to
introduce it in evidence,
Mr. Ehrmantraut will make himself
available to the defense,
and he will set
the record straight.
Categorically
and unequivocally.
Did he threaten you,
or pay you off?
Whoa! Okay, that's it.
We are done. Let's go.
You're doing the right thing.
This Salamanca character?
Maniac.
I had my own...
thing with him.
I didn't wanna say before,
because conflict of interest,
yadda yadda,
but, yeah, he's nuts.
I'm talking,
he had me hog-tied in
the desert with
a gun to my head.
Broke two guys' legs,
right in front of me.
If I hadn't talked him down,
he probably would've...
I'll spare you the gory details,
but it was a deal and a half.
Not something you forget.
And you're
telling me this, why?
Don't be too tough on yourself.
Like they say, discretion is
the better part of velour.
I would've done the same thing!
Hey, today, it's on me.
No charge.
You take the next one.
And bill me.
Ingrate.
Hey, Jimmy.
Did you tell Howard yet?
I can't really talk right now.
You didn't tell him.
No. And I won't
until it's rock solid.
Like,
offer-letter-in-hand solid.
When are you gonna get
that offer letter?
I'm guessing next Thursday, after
my interview with the partners.
Yeah, but that's just
a formality, right?
Basically. I hope.
What's the offer, you think?
I mean, brass tacks.
Well,
it's not gonna be as plush
as your deal at Davis and Main,
but they'll make me partner
in two years.
As opposed to somewhere between
five years and never at HHM.
Not too shabby.
Yeah. And then
there's my law school loans.
What is that,
a couple of grand by now?
I wish. I had to finance
the whole thing,
and was only making mail room money.
I've got like 15,000 left.
Wow. Schweikart
wants you bad?
Jimmy, did you have
something you needed?
No, no. Just checking in.
I'll see you later, okay?
If you play your cards right.
Bye.
Omar! Where are you?
Omar, would you be so kind
as to take a letter for me?
"Dearest Clifford..."
No, that's too much.
"Dear Cliff..." What do you
think, "Clifford" or "Cliff"?
I don't... It depends
on what the letter is.
It's just fine. Treat yourself.
"Dear" whoever you put in.
Continuing.
"My heart is heavy as..."
No, it sounds like
a medical condition.
Let's go with
"It is with a heavy heart."
Okay?
"It is with a heavy heart"
"that I tender my resignation
to Davis and Main."
"Tender" is better
than "submit," yeah?
Resignation?
Yes, sir.
So, "Tender, blah blah blah,
to Davis and Main."
"These have been,
some of the most"
"professionally satisfying
days of my life."
What's wrong? You think I'm
laying it on too thick?
No, um...
I just didn't realize
how unhappy you were here.
Not unhappy, per se.
More like, not happy.
I had no idea.
It's not your fault, buddy.
You're top notch.
Where were we?
It's just you worked
so hard to get here,
and it's so much to give up.
I mean, the perks alone...
Yeah, the apartment is...
Yeah.
And the car.
For the most part,
the car's pretty sweet.
And the bonus.
The bonus is a done deal.
They already cut me the check.
I get to keep the bonus.
Not if you quit.
Before a certain term,
I think yours is a year?
You have to pay the money back.
It's, um...
Yeah, um...
Yeah,
I think it's right there.
Yeah.
Omar, that...
That whole
letter of resignation thing?
I didn't mean that.
Not a word. I...
I... I'm so incredibly
stressed out.
I'm stressed out the wazoo.
I...
To be honest, it's been
more of an adjustment
than I expected
here at Davis and Main.
So, I just... Don't repeat
what I said to anyone.
I figured something had to be wrong.
Really wrong.
Because you like
it here, right?
I love it.
Call it a momentary
lapse of reason.
Let's just rewind the tape
and you know,
forget this happened.
Mum's the word. No problem.
I feel better already.
You know, sometimes, you have
to say something out loud
to hear how crazy it sounds.
Thank you, Omar.
Hi, Jimmy McGill.
Jimmy, this is Al Newman
of Allied Funeral Homes.
Great to meet you, Al.
Nice tie.
Thanks.
All right, let's get
started, shall we?
What are you doing?
Hey, Doug, got a
juicer for the office.
Jimmy, it's very loud.
Brian, come on in.
We have clients out there.
Sure, you can. Two! Coming right up.
Jimmy...
Sometimes, it gets a little jammed.
You just gotta force it.
Shit!
I'm...
I'm spreading it around.
Did I get you? Nah.
Now I got you with this.
Chrissakes, Jimmy!
Backwards only.
Solo backward-o, yeah?
Because we got suction
that way.
Leverage. It's physics.
El physico!
Don Clifford wants his floors clean.
Limpio, limpar.
Comprende?
Dude, I'm from Michigan.
So, you don't understand
a word I've been saying?
What...
Good night.
No, you try. Backwards.
Excuse me?
Can I have everyone's
attention, please?
Everyone can hear me? Good.
Frankly,
this is not a conversation
I ever thought I would have
in my professional career.
But it's been
brought to my attention
that we have an ongoing
situation in the washroom.
Someone's not flushing.
Once is an accident,
maybe even twice.
Three times?
No, that's a pattern.
And we're not talking
about a number one!
Yes, thank you, Erin.
Now, I'm not here
to shame anyone.
Nor do I even want to know
who did it, but...
Cliff? It was me.
Jimmy, I just said
I didn't wanna know.
Hey, we need the water.
I read somewhere
that the Santa Fe watershed
is down two full
inches this year!
Every time you flush a toilet,
you waste a gallon of water.
A gallon, what could
be greener than this?
They're low-flow toilets,
Jimmy. From now on, flush.
Low-flow, that's good.
Good thinking.
What is that?
Jimmy?
What's going on in there?
Jimmy!
You can hear this
through the door?
I didn't realize, I'm sorry.
What do you think you're doing?
I took your advice.
I'm blowing off steam.
"Blowing off steam"?
Yeah. Like you and
your guitar, you know?
I gotta say, you're right. I
mean, it really helps with stress.
I know, I don't sound very
good, but I'm just learning.
I heard that the key is, you
have to keep this bag inflated.
Enough!
Put that down.
Now, I want you in my office.
You win.
What do I win?
You're fired.
What? Cliff, if this is
about the bagpipes...
It's not about the bagpipes.
Well, of course,
it's the bagpipes.
It's the bagpipes and it's
the not flushing and this,
and this optical migraine you call
a business suit! It's about...
It's about you keeping your bonus.
That's what this is about!
Been brushing up on your
contract law, haven't you?
You want outta here, clearly,
but you can't just up and quit
and expect to keep your bonus.
And if I fire you for cause
like I should have done for the
TV commercial, again, no bonus.
However, if I fire you
not for cause,
but for being
an all-around jackass,
yeah, hurray for you.
If you think there's been
some malfeasance here...
Save it.
I could fight you on this,
but you're not worth my time.
I'd rather just have you gone.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
I'll just...
pack up.
First,
do me the favor of not treating
me like a fool for once.
Tell me, how exactly
did I mistreat you?
What did I do to deserve
this kind of behavior?
We gave you opportunities.
Encouraged you to excel.
We got you a car, an apartment.
Hell, that cocobolo desk!
Do you see a desk like that in here?
You never gave this a chance.
Why?
I tried to make it work.
Really, I did. I'm just...
A square peg.
If you knew that,
why did you take the job?
I'm sorry.
How much was the desk?
$7,000.
I'll write you a check.
Fine. For whatever good
that does.
Take your desk and get out.
Hey, Cliff, for what it's worth?
I think you're a good guy.
For what it's worth,
I think you're an asshole.
Hey!
Yeah. It's open.
Jimmy?
Hey. Can I talk to
you for a minute?
Does Howard know you're here?
God, no. I snuck in.
Yeah, but make it quick.
Actually, can we talk
in the conference room?
Why?
It's just more appropriate.
No one's gonna need it till 4:00.
I checked.
Please. Ten minutes, tops.
After you.
Have a seat.
What... What's going on?
Spill it.
Okay.
Schweikart & Cokely
will pay your debt to HHM
and make you a partner
in two years. Correct?
Apparently.
That's the deal, yes. Why?
Would you
entertain a better offer?
From whom? HHM?
From me.
I'll make you
a partner tomorrow.
Consider that proof of concept.
Wexler-McGill, Partners at Law.
You and me, together.
If Schweikart can pay
your debt, so can I.
And with my signing bonus,
you'll have a clean slate.
Sky's the limit.
Hey, we're good together.
You know that.
So, what's stopping us?
Let's jump in with both feet.
Be our own bosses.
Build our own future.
"Be our own bosses."
What about clients?
Mesa Verde just signed
with you, didn't they?
It'll be a hard sell
to take them with me.
Then there'll be
another Mesa Verde.
That was all you, Kim. You did
it once, you can do it again.
You make it sound easy. No.
You're talking to a guy who lived
in the back of a nail salon.
This is gonna be a whole lot
of blood, sweat and tears.
At least at the start.
But in the end, we'll have a
practice that is 100% ours.
That's worth it.
Or we fail and we end up
with nothing.
You're right. It's a gamble.
It's a big one.
Yeah, but you're
betting on yourself,
and from where I sit,
the odds are in your favor.
You are an amazing lawyer.
This is your chance
to show the world that.
So, why not go to Schweikart?
They'll make me partner, and
they're a solid, respectable firm.
You can't deny that.
You deserve more
than just a lateral move.
Bottom line, that's what
Schweikart represents.
He's just Howard Hamlin
by a different name.
You keep talking
about me and Schweikart.
What about you
and Davis and Main?
It's over. I quit today.
Technically, I got fired.
What happened?
It was mutual,
and a long time coming.
That job was never the
right fit for me. This is.
If we're going to be law partners,
I need to know one thing.
What kind of lawyer
are you going to be?
I don't mean what kind of law you're
going to practice, I mean...
Are you going to
play it straight,
or are you going
to be colorful?
I'm gonna play it straight.
Right down the line.
I'm gonna dot every "I"
and I'm gonna cross every...
There's no point in me doing
this if I can't be myself.
Every time I try to do
things someone else's way,
it blows up in my face. That's
what happened at Davis and Main,
look how that turned out.
I almost derailed your career.
Pissed everyone off.
I've been trying to be the person
someone else wants me to be
for I don't know how long.
First it was Chuck.
Then it was you.
And that's not your fault.
That was my choice.
But if we're gonna do this,
I gotta go into it as me.
So, yeah.
Colorful. I guess.
What do you say?
I just...
I don't see why it's so important
to you that we work together.
I mean, we're already...
Why do you need me for this?
I don't need you.
I want you.
You've got me.
Just not as a law partner.
I have to get back to work.
You okay?
Yeah. No, I'm fine.
Go on.
I'll see you later?
Yeah.
It's move-in ready,
as you can see.
And they've renovated
within the past three years.
New floors, new kitchen...
And it's a good
amount of space.
It's not too much house,
you think?
No, not at all.
And look at that backyard!
They're leaving the playhouse.
Isn't that amazing?
Kaylee will go crazy for that.
You'll never get
her outta there.
I know, right?
And the most important part,
the schools are good and
the neighborhood is great.
I called the local precinct
and asked about crime stats,
they're some of the lowest
in the city.
Plus, I got a good
vibe from him.
They sounded really responsive.
Sounds perfect.
Yeah.
Do you like it?
If you're happy, I'm happy.
Yeah. I do.
But... I'm... But what?
It's a lot of money.
I know, I'm like a broken record.
But it is.
You don't worry about that. We'll make it happen.
Whatever the cost.
Mike, I... I'm serious.
Not another thought.
If you want it, it's yours.
How are we looking?
It's perfect.
Let's do it. Fantastic!
Do you have another hour? We
could go down to the office,
get the pre-approval
in order, all that.
Sounds good.
We'll meet you there.
Sure. See you in a few.
I feel like I can
finally breathe.
Good. I'm glad.
You wanna ride together?
No, I'll follow you over.
Car looks good. Wouldn't even
know you so much as scratched it.
Yeah, um,
my guy knows his stuff.
Thank you, Pop. For everything.
You go on now.
I'll see you there.
Okay.
Right here.
Sorry, I almost
lost you at that light.
No problem.
Watch the fish tank.
On the left.
My left. My left.
There.
What do you think?
Yeah.
It's, um...
What should I do with this?
Dump it on
the side of the road.
That's where I got it
in the first place.
Hey, buddy.
This is over and above.
No, it's okay. Really.
How about a drink?
I know I could use one.
Come on, I'm buying.
Nah, I'm good. Long drive.
Cucumber water for the road?
I'm totally set. Thank you.
Gotta get home to my kids.
How about you?
What are you gonna do now?
Onward and upward.
Thanks, Omar. Drive safe.
Hello!
You've reached the law offices
of James M. McGill, Esq.
Kindly leave...
Hi, you've reached
the law offices of Jimmy McGill.
Please leave a message,
and I'll get back to you
as soon as I can. Thanks.
Summary judgments, yes.
I've handled six.
Actually, one recently
was quite complex.
It was a litigation,
the result of a nasty divorce.
My client was suing
her former company,
which she and her ex had
split in their settlement.
The issues involved had me
chasing case law for weeks.
Who heard it? Judge Pittman.
That guy. He's a handful?
Well, he can be a tough nut to
crack, but he did rule in my favor.
All right, enough about law,
law, law.
We know you're good.
We know you know your stuff.
Tell us about Kim Wexler.
You started in the mail room,
is that right?
I did. I was there almost,
well, 10 years ago now.
Pulled yourself up by
your bootstraps. I like that.
I see you went to UNM Law,
are you from New Mexico?
Not originally.
I'm from the Midwest.
A tiny little town,
barely on the map.
Near the
Kansas-Nebraska border.
You've never heard of it.
So, what brought you here?
I guess...
One day, I just looked around
at my life, at who I was.
And I realized if I kept
going the way I was going...
Which way was that?
Best-case,
probably married to the guy
that ran the town gas station.
Maybe cashiering down at the Hinky Dinky.
- The "Hinky" what?
- Hinky Dinky.
It was our supermarket.
Um...
I just wanted something else.
What did you want?
More.
Thanks for coming by.
Always a pleasure.
- Great to put a face to the name.
- Thanks.
We're gonna put our
heads together and discuss.
But I feel safe to say that you
can expect to hear from us
by tomorrow at the latest.
That's...
Fantastic.
I look forward to it.
We liked you when you came in here.
We like you more now.
Well, thank you so much
for taking the time.
And I will,
speak to you soon.
It was great to meet you, Lynne.
You, too.
Perry. Pleasure, Kim.
Howard. It's Rich, actually.
My God, I'm so sorry.
No, no.
I'm happy to be
confused with Howard.
He's a damn good-looking man!
Don't worry about it.
Come on, I'll walk you out.
Hi. I'm here to see Jimmy.
He's in a meeting.
A meeting? Have a seat.
And listen,
I don't ever want to hear
the word "permit" again.
Capisce?
Your funeral, dude.
Hey! What are you doing here?
Just in the neighborhood.
Great!
And I want
a dolly this time.
What kind?
Western? Hustler, peewee?
Hey, watch your mouth
around the lady.
How the hell should I know?
You're the nerd.
Just make it cheap.
Now go on, get outta here.
I see you got
your old car back.
Yep. The kidney people
wouldn't take it.
Sorry.
Well, you finally
got your cocobolo desk.
Finally got my cocobolo desk.
Feel like it's a good omen
for what's next.
And what's that?
This!
Solo practice.
Being my own man again.
So, how'd it go
with Schweikart?
Went well.
Should be getting
their offer tomorrow.
That's fantastic!
I'm really happy for you.
Thanks.
You know, we should celebrate.
Whataburger! On me!
I'm not taking the job.
Why not? You were right.
It's time for me to be my own boss.
Solo practice.
What, you don't think
it's a good idea now?
Don't tell me
you've changed your mind.
No, I... I'm surprised, is all.
Hey, I've said all along you're
too good for those clowns.
This is...
Shit, yeah. Wow. It's great!
Good. To that end,
I have a pitch for you.
Not Wexler-McGill.
But Wexler
and McGill.
We find an office,
share the housekeeping costs,
the rent,
electricity, everything.
But I am Kim Wexler,
attorney at law,
and you are Jimmy McGill,
attorney at law.
Both free to
practice as we see fit.
Separate firms under one roof.
We're both headed uptown,
so why can't we share a taxi?
You do things your way
and I do them mine.
We'll have freedom, but we aren't
each trying to go it alone.
Not partners.
Solo practitioners together.
What do you think?
I don't know what to say.
Say yes.