[Chuck sighs]
[Metronome ticking]
["Sicilienne" plays]
[Discordant note plays, music stops]
[Ticking continues]
["Sicilienne" plays]
[Discordant note plays, music stops]
[Ticking continues]
[Knock on door]
[Ticking stops]
- Howard.
- Morning!
Delivery for McGill.
[Chuckling] What're you doing here?
Ah, it's been a while.
Thought I should come in and check on you.
Did I hear music?
- Hmm?
- No, no.
I was just... ‭let me get that for you.
[Grunts]
- Good to see you, Howard.
- Oh, likewise.
You are sorely missed, my friend.
Don't take that as any undo pressure.
Um, I'm thinking of maybe coming in
for an hour or two next week.
Maybe kind of play it by ear.
Well, ‭I-if you feel comfortable.
I mean, we certainly
would love to have you.
We will take anything we can get.
I'll figure out a day and get
Ernesto to give you a heads up.
That sounds great.
[Ice clatters]
How's Ernie working out?
Uh, he's been fine, for the most part.
Excellent.
Everything on track with, uh, Sandpiper?
Moving along.
Davis & Main are, uh...
really pulling their weight.
Well, they better.
It's a complex case.
Well, it's definitely not
a two-man job, that's for sure.
Anyone, uh, heard from Jimmy?
I have, yes. I've talked to him.
How is he?
Howard: He's fine.
Doing well.
Speaking of which... I have some news.
He's working at Davis & Main.
Doing what?
Oh, working as an attorney.
Hm.
Clifford Main hired Jimmy?
Mm-hmm.
To be fair, he had his doubts,
but he's giving Jimmy a chance.
He had his own people
doing client outreach,
but every time they would talk
to a Sandpiper resident,
Jimmy's name would come up.
You know, he... [sighs]
- Those old folks, they just...
- They love him.
Yeah, they do. ‭mm-hmm.
Plus, I guess Cliff thought
it would be a good idea
for the case to have that sort of, uh...
You know... continuity.
Mm.
Jimmy certainly has a way with people.
He does.
[Inhales deeply]
They're aware of his background
at Davis & Main?
His education?
In the spirit of full disclosure,
Cliff did talk to me beforehand.
I didn't pull any punches.
I tried to paint a complete picture.
But I didn't stand in the way.
Of course not.
Nor should you.
Truth be told...
Kim Wexler pushed for this... hard.
But I didn't, uh,
you know, stand in the way.
Partner track?
I would, uh...
Yeah.
Assume so.
[Chuckles] That's great.
Good for Jimmy.
[Chuckles] Charlie Hustle, right?
Yep.
[Both chuckle] ‭Yep.
Well, I'll get out of your hair.
Anything else you need me
to add to Ernie's list?
No. All set. All good.
Thanks for coming by, Howard.
Any time. You truly are missed.
No pressure.
[Chuckles]
[Door opens, closes]
[Metronome ticking]
♪
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
Resync by Se7enOfNin9
www.addic7ed.com
Francis: Document review
will be coordinated through HHM.
To date, the following documents
have been requested from Sandpiper
as part of our initial discovery petition.
One... resident lease
agreements, past and present,
from all Sandpiper locations.
Two... invoices and transaction documents
from all supply companies
used by Sandpiper.
Three... list of all past and present
official Sandpiper vendors.
Four... any and all business
agreements and contracts
between Sandpiper and its distributors.
Five... records of residents'
social security check receipts.
Six... allowance transaction statements.
Seven... resident invoices
non-related to sup...
Kim: I'm loving the new look.
How's Santa Fe?
[Chuckling] It's, uh...
[chuckles] It's... It's really...
See? What'd I tell you?
- Nice place?
- [Scoffs]
The finest in temporary corporate housing.
[Chuckles] Can't wait to see it.
Maybe I should leave HHM.
Get on that cushy D&M train.
It is very cushy.
It's amazing.
Jimmy...
I'm so happy for you.
Thanks.
You know, things are really turning around.
I'm even thinking of looking, you know,
my own place to buy.
- In Santa Fe?
- Not sure yet.
Maybe someplace, uh, closer to Albuquerque
since I'm going between the two so much.
Okay.
So, halfway points.
Um... ‭yeah, I was thinking, uh...
- Oh, wait, what about Corrales?
- Corrales.
Yeah, get a nice, little bungalow,
or maybe not so little.
Big, open floor plan.
I don't want any walls
disrupting my chi, yeah.
Uh, but I'm thinking I definitely want
some decent acreage,
get in touch with nature.
Horses.
Come on. You could get horses.
Man, that would be so amazing.
Too expensive. They, uh,
all the oats... right?
It's oats ‭that they're always eating?
It's worth it. ‭and the horseshoes.
You have to get them shoes
and nail them with a hammer.
- It's totally worth it.
- It's...
Long ride through the country
and then glass of wine
on the back patio at sunset.
Oh, we should get one of those smokers.
We could just barbecue for days.
Yeah. We definitely
‭[blows] got to get a smoker.
[Chuckles softly]
All right, well...
I got to go to the salon.
They're delivering my new company car.
Ugh, are you serious?
- What?
- [Scoffs]
Jeeves, ‭where's my solid-gold blimp?
No, not that one. The other one.
Jealous.
- [Car door opens]
- Totally.
Oh, I forgot.
‭I got you a present. One sec.
[Car alarm chirps]
[Bag rustles]
[Chuckles] Such a beautiful wrapping job.
It's a shame to open it.
It's a gift. Be grateful.
Just keeping it real.
Come on.
Second is still very, very good.
All right.
Thanks.
See you tonight?
Maybe.
If you play your cards right.
[Keys jingle]
[Women speaking vietnamese]
[Winch whirring]
Hello, beautiful.
What do you think, ladies?
[Women speaking vietnamese]
Yeah, I know, right?
It's got all leather interior,
heated seats for those
cold desert mornings.
This must be what heaven looks like.
[Speaks Vietnamese]
Hey!
Goodbye hug?
No?
[Chuckling] All right,
well, forgo the tears
and just say, "till we meet again."
[Speaks Vietnamese]
[Tow truck idling]
[Sighs]
[Clink]
[Clinking]
Must be metric.
[Engine starts]
[Tires screech]
[Rattling]
[Rumbling]
[Seatbelt unclicks]
Hey!
[Beep]
[Engine revs]
What... [Chuckles]
What are you doing here?
I work here.
Oh. Small world.
So, is this the parking lot
for the police station?
It is.
You don't know if they validate, do you?
Why don't you pull around over there,
and we'll have a little talk.
Uh, okay.
[Sighs]
Why are you here?
I... I have business with the police.
And what business might that be?
Well, if you must know, I was robbed.
Somebody broke into my house
and stole my property.
Your drugs.
Yeah, but obviously
‭I didn't tell the cops that.
I'm not stupid.
You've already spoken to them?
A couple of them came by my house.
But it's not the drugs that I care about.
I mean, I care.
It's my baseball cards
I need back.
- Your baseball cards?
- Yes.
I have a very valuable
collection of baseball cards,
and someone stole them.
I guess I shouldn't be surprised
I have to tell you this.
But it's probably a bad idea
that you willingly talk to the police,
being a criminal and all.
I'm not here as a criminal.
I'm here as a crime victim.
Just because I occasionally sell
some pharmaceuticals,
I no longer have a right
to protection from crime?
And I was very careful
when I talked to them.
I... they have no idea
about my other business.
If you already made your report,
why are you here?
They called me.
They have a few more questions.
They are very dedicated
to finding this thief.
Since you're new to this,
let me explain it to you.
They've invited you on a fishing trip.
What's that? A fishing trip?
Those cops have no interest in
helping you get your cards back.
You're obviously under suspicion.
There was nothing there for them to see.
I refer you ‭to our previous conversation
and this blinking neon sign of a
vehicle that says "drug dealer."
They suspect you.
They will get you in there,
pretend to be your friend,
lull you into a false sense of security,
and then they will sweat you.
And you will break.
I don't... I... [Chuckles]
I disagree.
Not open for debate. You go home now.
But I have an appointment.
Break it.
And if they call you,
do not answer the phone.
But what about my baseball cards?
- Cost of doing business.
- No!
No, no, no!
I am getting those back!
I will take the risk!
No, you won't.
Because then you'll be putting
my well-being at risk.
I have to!
I... I... [Sighs]
Those cards?
Some of them were my dad's.
I... I am getting them back.
I'm getting them back.
[Siren wails in distance]
I'll find your cards.
Is... ser...
is that something you do?
Wow, that's...
That is so generous of you.
Oh, it'll cost you.
Oh.
Okay, uh...
We should discuss some sort
of financial arrangement
in which I... I, uh...
Oh.
Okay, then!
Jesus.
[Scribbling]
[Indistinct conversations in distance]
[Guitar playing in distance]
[Indistinct conversations continue]
[Guitar continues]
[Guitar stops]
Come on in.
I didn't mean to interrupt.
Not at all. I was just
blowing off some steam.
- You sound good.
- Thank you.
Clears the head. You play?
Oh, I tried to learn in high school,
but then I decided there were
easier ways to get girls.
[Chuckles] Well, I hope
you've got a way to decompress.
Everybody needs something.
How you settling in?
Great.
Uh, it's... ‭it's quite a step up for me.
Well, we're happy to have you.
Just let us know if there's
anything else you need, Jimmy.
Thanks... Cliff.
Um, I'm happy to be here.
Great.
Uh, better get back to it.
Yeah, me, too, I suppose.
Um...
Actually, um, ‭I might
have found something
in the initial disclosures.
Oh, yeah? Schweikart and
Cokely keep referring to
the "optional allowance program,"
but I checked a number
of residents' contracts.
Not a single one has opted out,
which makes me think
it's more of a mandatory
financial arrangement.
And you're thinking that's
the "failure to state a claim"
that they filed in their answer?
They keep saying it's optional,
thereby voluntary.
I think we can counter that
if "opting in" is a requirement
for residency,
which it sure seems to be,
well, their voluntary claims
don't hold water.
Might be on to something here.
Nice work, Jimmy.
Thanks, Cliff.
♪
- [Door bell jingles]
- Hola.
Hola. ¿cómo estás?
Welcome. How can I help you?
Um, I was hoping to get an estimate.
Uh, mi car. Mi coche.
You do cars?
Sí. Cars. Todo el tiempo. ‭ah.
I... I was hoping to get
my seats reupholstered.
Um... Mm.
Um, take a look? ¿mira?
[Stammers, speaks Spanish]
[Conversing in Spanish]
- Un momento.
- Sí, sí, sí, sí.
[Speaks Spanish]
[Door bell jingles]
Gracias.
Yeah.
Thinking something new.
Give the old girl a little love.
[Speaking Spanish]
[Chuckles]
He said you should save
your money and get a new car.
Yeah? Well, it has a sentimental value.
[Speaking Spanish]
- [Chuckles] Classic car.
- Mmm.
[Speaking Spanish]
Um, what material do you want?
Well, I was thinking leather, definitely.
Uh, maybe alligator.
[Chuckles]
[Speaking Spanish]
[Chuckles] Señor. Too much money.
Yeah, but like I said,
it has a sentimental value.
[Speaking Spanish]
He says, uh, alligator's
gonna look all wrong.
Cheaper might be better.
Well, show me what you'd pick.
[Stammering]
[Ringing] Ooh. I'm sorry, señor.
Uh, my son... He...
He will help you, okay?
[Speaks Spanish]
-
Ah, mucho gusto.
[Ringing continues]
[Sniffs]
How'd you find me?
[Scoffs]
[Sniffs]
Why are you here?
Baseball cards.
The way I figure, you saw that
mid-life crisis of a vehicle
and wisely decided
‭to cut ties with the man,
and I don't blame you... I did, too.
And then you ripped him off.
And I'm sure those baseball cards
looked like an easy way
to make a few extra bucks
off that idiot, teach him a lesson, too.
But you underestimated
just how big an idiot
you were dealing with.
[Chuckles] No, I am pretty aware.
Well, then, you underestimated
how attached the man was to those cards...
so attached, he called the police
and reported them stolen.
Now they're nosing around.
That sounds like a "you" problem.
No, I think it's very much an "us" problem.
Yeah, I guess I'll just
have to take my chances.
But [Whistles] Good luck to you.
You know, I was hoping
you'd see our dilemma
and do the right thing.
But I think what we have here now
is a carrot-and-stick situation.
Oh, yeah?
This the stick? Hmm?
You coming here, threatening my family?
Huh?
'Cause you're gonna need
a bigger stick, old man.
I'm not here to threaten your family.
And the name of the stick
is Tuco Salamanca.
Now, you don't play ball, so to speak,
and Tuco finds out about
your little side business.
That a big enough stick?
However, I prefer the carrot.
I think you will, too.
And what would that be?
You give me back the baseball cards,
$10,000 in cash,
and you net roughly... roughly... $60,000.
[Chuckles]
And how exactly does that work?
[Door opens]
[Door closes]
Chuck: Ernesto?
Hey.
Going somewhere?
Yes, we are.
Pryce: She's a little tricky
around the corners.
So...
and you got to go with the premium gas.
I know it seems like a scam,
but it makes a huge difference.
And I would get her washed
at least once a week.
And spring for the hand wax.
You're gonna want that
extra layer of protection
for the clear coat.
[Sighs]
She deserves the best.
I'll make sure the boys at the chop shop
are real gentle with her.
Wait. W-why?
No.
You think I'd be caught dead
driving that thing?
It looks like a school bus
for 6-year-old pimps.
All right, shall we move this along?
[Trunk opens]
Aaron.
Okay, there's Jeter.
All right. Okay.
[Sighs]
Mantle. Mantle. There's Mantle.
- [Chuckles]
- We good?
Uh, yeah, that looks like everyone.
Yeah, they're here.
‭looks like everyone's here.
And now the other item.
And now our business is concluded.
[Keys jingle]
[Engine starts]
[Engine revs]
You know, I can't help thinking
an apology was in order.
[Cellphone rings "Take Me Out
to the Ball Game"]
Uh, it's... it's the police again.
Sandpiper hasn't really responded
to our discovery requests.
They've buried us in paperwork,
but nothing actually relevant
to the particulars in this case.
No real surprise there.
We may have to subpoena their bank records.
Thank you, Erin.
Jimmy.
How we doing with client outreach?
Oh, while we're waiting on those subpoenas,
I'm thinking we should t
wrangling some of this stuff
from the clients themselves.
Most of these folks
have hard copies of everything
going back to the
Eisenhower administration.
Of course, given some of their, uh...
Inconsistent organizational practices,
- it's gonna be slow going.
- [Knock on door]
I'm so sorry to interrupt.
Uh, this one lady, um, she's sweet,
but, uh, deaf as a doornail.
She keeps all of her paperwork
in, um, she keeps it...
I'm sorry. Excuse me, Jimmy.
I'm gonna need everybody's phone,
key fobs, and electronics.
Chuck. Welcome.
Please. Have a seat.
Don't mind me.
Hey, everybody.
[Clears throat]
Sorry for the interruption.
Just pretend I'm not here.
Happy to have you.
Jimmy, where were we?
Uh, yeah.
So, I was saying...
Um...
Uh, getting the documents
from some of the clients...
We definitely have some pack rats.
God bless 'em.
I was visiting Mrs. Gusdorff
at, uh, Sandpiper Santa Fe,
and I spent the whole afternoon
sorting through just a haystack
of recipes and half-off coupons
from big lots.
But now we've got copies of
this woman's monthly statements
going back to March 1997,
so it might be a little labor-intensive,
but our clients will always be
our best resource.
Plus, they have ribbon candy.
[Light laughter]
Chuck: Jimmy.
Hello?
What are you doing here?
[Sighs] ‭My name is on the building.
So great to have you here.
If you need anything, I'll be in my office.
[Sighs]
Why are you here?
To bear witness.
[Cellphone rings]
James McGill.
It's Ehrmantraut. [Sighs]
You still morally flexible?
If so, I might have a job for you.
Where and when?
Take a seat.
Mr. Wormald, thank you
for coming in and talking to us.
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, we've been looking at the reports
that the officers took at the scene,
and we have a few
‭small follow-up questions.
Uh, sorry to waste your time.
Just standard stuff.
There's really no need
for a lawyer to be here.
I'm here in more of an advisory capacity.
Dan just, uh, wanted
a friendly face next to him.
Coleman: ‭Well, we're all friendly here.
Look at us. Four friends.
[Chuckles]
We just want to get the facts straight
so we can, um, help you get
your property for you.
Yeah, you know, uh, it's fine.
Uh, yeah, there's no need to, uh...
No, it's just standard procedure.
You know, ‭officers don't always get
all the information we
need in their report.
We just want to find the guys
who took your baseball cards.
Yeah, that's, uh...
You know, my uncle
‭had a Ty Cobb tobacco card.
Kept that thing behind six inches of glass
like it was the Mona Lisa or something.
Wow. Ty Cobb?
Tell him to keep the lights low.
Even artificial lighting
has a certain amount
of ultraviolet radiation
that can, uh, you know...
- Over the long term...
- Yeah.
Um, can you just remind us
exactly where you kept
your cards in the house?
Yeah, well, uh, as I was trying
to say, it's no longer an issue.
I found them.
So you found the cards?
Uh, yep.
I just wanted to come down and
tell you, you know, in person.
You found them?
Where? Around the house?
No. I, uh, I hired a private investigator,
and he tracked them down.
So, yeah.
Really? So, where were they?
You know, it's fine. It is.
I really... I ought to
get out of your hair.
Uh, you've wasted enough time on me.
No, no, it's... ‭it's okay. It's our job.
We just want to get the facts right
so we can help close this case for you.
It's done.
Case closed!
I just... I know how much, you know,
you guys have on your hands,
like murderers and robbers
and gangs and stuff. I...
Hey, Danny, ‭why don't you get some air?
You can have some coffee.
I'll finish up ‭with the detectives here.
Okay, let's get down
to brass tacks here, guys.
I'm guessing your two
fine uniformed officers
found Mr. Wormald's little hidey hole,
and that's why you two are so interested
in "helping" my friend here.
I get it.
A hiding place in the baseboard...
it's gonna make anyone suspicious.
But let me assure you there's
nothing illegal going on here.
Then why is he so nervous?
Mm-hmm. 'Cause I must say, the
flop sweat is kind of suspect.
We all have our secrets, don't we?
And who among us is without sin?
But those sins aren't all
of the criminal variety,
and neither are Mr. Wormald's, okay?
They are, however, very private.
Private, like drug dealer, maybe?
No, no!
He's being evasive because
it's a sensitive subject,
very delicate, and of no concern
to law enforcement.
You know, as much as we'd love
to, um, take your word for it,
we're gonna need a little more than that.
All right, well, this all comes
down to a personal dispute.
That's all.
It's... it's between, um, Mr. Wormald
and, uh... his art patron.
- "Art patron"?
- Yeah.
Uh, my client has an arrangement
with a wealthy gentleman
for whom [clears throat]
Mr. Wormald provides...
Art in exchange for
‭this gentleman's generous, uh...
We'll call it patronage.
Art? Like... like what? Paintings?
It's more like digital media.
Digital media?
He made videos for the man.
What kind of videos?
Private videos of an artistic nature.
That's what was in the hiding place.
That's what it's for.
So, this art patron stole the
videos and the baseball cards?
Well, there was a misunderstanding.
I mean, uh, ‭call it creative differences.
Artists are volatile creatures.
[Sighs]
Guys, this all comes down
to just a lovers' spat, okay?
Two consenting adults had a falling out.
That happens.
And the, uh, "patron" stole the videos
and the baseball cards, uh,
to "make a point," I guess.
But the headline here is, it's all settled.
Hearts have mended,
and Mr. Wormald will not
be pressing charges.
What was on these videos?
- They were private.
- You've said that.
[Sighs]
They were videos intended
to titillate the senses.
- Okay, so porn.
- Not... no.
Not as such.
Technically, they would be
categorized as fetish videos.
But nothing illegal.
Just a man... a fully
clothed man, I might add...
just all by himself.
Just... just Mr. Wormald
fully clothed, uh, yeah.
So... all right.
So, fully clothed Mr. Wormald
by himself doing what?
Yeah, come on, man. What?
[Sighs] Squat cobbler.
What's a s-squat cobbler?
Squat cobbler.
‭You know what squat cobbler is.
No, I don't... I don't know
what a squat cobbler is.
No, me neither. What is it?
What? And you two guys are cops?
Hoboken squat cobbler.
Full moon moon-pie.
Boston cream splat. [Chuckles]
Seriously?
Simple-Simon-the-ass-man.
Dutch apple ass.
Guys, am I not speaking English here?
What the hell is a squat cobbler?!
It's when a man sits in pie!
He sits in a pie!
And he... he wiggles around.
Maybe it's like hellmann's mayonnaise.
It has a different name
west of the rockies.
I don't know. But, uh, technically,
he does a crybaby squat, so there's tears,
which makes it more specialized.
Not all pie sitters cry.
But I'm gonna tell you something.
This guy is a regular Julianne Moore
once he gets ‭the waterworks cranked up.
Pies?
What? Like apple?
Guys, I'm not ‭the
filmmaker here, all right?
Banana cream. I... uh, peach.
Oh, and there... And there
is a costume involved.
[Snorts]
You got to be shitting us.
Yeah, like I would make this up.
Hey, the world is
‭a rich tapestry, my friends.
But trust me on this.
You don't want to see it.
[Chuckles]
So, uh, we're good, right?
Yeah. Great. [Chuckles]
There is, however, one little,
tiny hanging Chad.
Well, what? What Chad?
You're gonna have to make a video.
[Keys jingle]
[Insects chirping]
[Grunts]
Kim: [Laughs] Wait. Wait.
So he eats the pies or just sits in them?
Both. Whatever you want.
Which comes first?
Uh, it's dealer's choice.
That's where the crying comes in, right?
That's a safe bet.
[Laughs]
How the hell ‭did you come up with that?
If you gave me a million years,
I still would not have come up with that.
The muse.
She speaks through me.
I am but a humble vessel.
And they bought it?
- Yeah.
- Wow.
I've heard some far-out
scenarios used to sow doubt,
but this definitely takes the cake.
Kim, Kim, Kim.
- Takes the pie.
- Yeah.
[Chuckling] Sorry.
I should just jump off the roof right now.
Yeah, you should feel bad about yourself.
Jesus, can you tell a story.
Well, to be fair, I think it was
the video that clinched it.
What video?
Wait, wait. You...
‭You actually made a video?
I got to say, in the end,
ol' Dan really committed.
I believed the tears.
Um, this is a leftover prop. It was extra.
I wasn't sure how many takes
we would need, so I over-bought,
but I promise you,
‭untouched by human buttocks.
You fabricated evidence?
I made a video.
Not exactly evidence.
You used it to exonerate a client.
You used falsified evidence
to exonerate a client.
Mm, I think you're splitting hairs.
I'm not splitting hairs.
What if Davis & Main find out
you faked evidence?
It wasn't a Davis & Main client.
It was some nothing, little pro-bono thing.
It was off the clock. It was,
uh, totally my own thing.
Why?
Why would you risk
‭the best job you've ever had
for some pro-bono case?
I was doing a favor for a friend.
Risking disbarment?
That's... that's some friend.
It's fine! It... it worked out.
Davis & Main are none the wiser.
Jimmy, ‭you're playing with fire here.
I didn't see you complaining
when, um, Ken the douchebag paid
our bar bill the other night.
No, that was a little bit
of rule breaking right there.
And if I remember correctly, you liked it.
A lot.
That is so not the same thing.
How? What's the difference?
That had nothing to do with work.
And we were just... just screwing around.
This?
Fabricating evidence.
Jimmy, ‭this could really hurt you.
If they find out, if you get caught...
It... they're never gonna find out.
Seriously? You sound like
every dumb criminal out there.
If you keep this up, they will find out.
- For what, Jimmy?
- ‭[Sighs]
What is the point?
[Clears throat]
I cannot hear ‭about this sort of thing.
Ever again. Okay?
I mean it, Jimmy.
You won't.
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
Resync by Se7enOfNin9
www.addic7ed.com