Okay. All set.
Thank you for your patience.
Didn't you say that the hearing
is more or less a formality?
Well, the real work's
already been done, yes.
In that case,
I'm fine covering it myself.
Kevin and Paige
don't need both of us there.
That may be strictly true,
but we want to send the right
message, don't we?
I'm just worried
about your comfort.
I find victory laps
very comforting.
Well done, my friend.
Good morning.
This meeting
of the New Mexico State Banking
Board is now in session.
We have Mesa Verde
here with us today,
and they're represented
by Charles McGill.
Nice to have you back, Charles.
Thank you. Good to be back.
I'm here with my colleague,
Howard Hamlin.
And may I introduce
Mr. Kevin Wachtell,
president and chairman
of Mesa Verde Holdings,
and Ms. Paige Novick,
Mesa Verde's senior counsel.
Hello and welcome.
I believe staff
has found the application
to meet the basic
requirements for approval.
That's right, isn't it?
With your permission,
Mr. Wachtell would like to make
a brief statement
in support of the application.
Mr. Commissioner, ladies and gentlemen
of the New Mexico Banking Board,
I'm honored and grateful to
appear before you this morning.
We believe that our
proposed expansion
is in the public interest,
both for Arizona and our own state.
For 46 years, the men and women
of Mesa Verde Bank and Trust
have prided ourselves
on personal service
and attention to detail,
second to none.
Mesa Verde continues to operate at
a Tier 1 leverage ratio of 11.2%.
- Uh... Hold on.
- And we feel...
Excuse me, Mr. Wachtell.
Just one moment.
Sir, sorry...
- What's going on?
- Well, let's find out.
Uh, Mr. Commissioner,
is there something we can clarify?
Um, yes. Can you give us the address of
the proposed Scottsdale branch again?
Certainly. It's 1216 Rosella Drive,
Scottsdale, Arizona, 85262.
1216?
Okay. Because the application
I'm looking at today
clearly gives the address as 1216.
1216. That's correct, sir.
But, in the original submission,
we're seeing, "1261 Rosella Drive."
- It is 1261.
- 1261.
I think, if you double check,
you'll see that 1216 is correct.
There seem to be two
different addresses here.
Mr. Commissioner, I have a
copy of our notice of intent,
which was published in newspapers
in Arizona and New Mexico.
It clearly states the address is 1261...
- Rosella Drive.
- Mr. Commissioner. It...it...
1261 Rosella Drive.
Yes, I have a copy of the
notice of intent, too.
But on the actual filing,
the address reads 1216.
So, which is it?
Mr. Commissioner,
if I may confer with my clients?
Certainly. Please.
It's absolutely 1261.
You are mistaken.
And with all due respect,
you are muddying the waters here.
Muddying the waters?
Look. Just look.
Well, this is clearly an error.
It's 1261.
I know where my own damn bank is.
Now, let's just all calm down.
I'm sure we can straighten this out.
I've got a building remodel
at 1261 Rosella.
I don't know where the hell 1216 is.
I... I don't quite understand.
- 1261?
- 1261.
- Is this gonna be a problem?
- No, I'm sure it won't be.
Um...
Mr. Commissioner, I apologize.
Unaccountably, there appears to
be a discrepancy in our filing.
So, the correct address
is the one that appeared
in the notice of intent?
The 1261?
It would seem so.
We'd like to request a, um...
An adjournment of just a few minutes,
so that we can amend the filing
to reflect the correct address.
Well, I, uh...
I can give you an adjournment, uh...
Uh, but, uh...
I don't think we can
get you back in today.
If I may,
when do you think you might
be able to schedule us?
I'm being told by staff
that they've already done the
research for 1216 Rosella Drive.
Our folks are going to have to
go back to square one...
- ...on the new address.
- If we could obtain
a provisional agreement today...
- to...to allow the branch to open...
- No, no.
With all due respect,
it's up to you folks
to submit accurate paperwork.
Maybe next time double check.
Now, uh, the soonest we
could revisit this matter...
Well, it looks like
six weeks from Friday.
We...
We can't wait six weeks.
Mr. Commissioner, Mesa Verde
has put effort and resources
into preparing this branch
to open immediately.
However unusual,
a provisional approval would be
most appreciated, most welcome.
- Time being of the essence...
- Charles, I'm sorry.
I'll see you in six weeks.
That closes the matter for today.
Will staff please note that Mesa
Verde will return in six weeks.
At which time, we will
revisit this application.
That's understood well now?
This is not possible.
This is not possible!
"1261."
No. No.
Chuck?
I don't understand.
It was 1216. It was.
I checked. I double checked!
Chuck, it happened.
Now we take our licks
and move on.
This doesn't just reflect on you.
An office full of associates
and paralegals let this get by.
I did too, for that matter.
It was 1216. I promise you!
Everyone makes mistakes.
This was no mistake.
I'm buying a round for the house.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Hey! Hey, listen up, everybody!
This gentleman's buying
a round for the house!
All right, lift with your knees.
What does that even mean?
"Lift with your knees?"
I don't know. It's something
sweaty people say. Here we go.
One, two, three.
Got it.
- Almost, almost, almost.
- Got it.
All right. Right there. Go. Go.
You okay?
Nothing a few years
of physical therapy won't fix.
Okay.
All right. Push.
Slow, slow, slow.
Corner, corner, corner.
Yeah. Get that one.
Hi, Paige, how are you?
Yeah. I mean, no. No, it's fine.
Uh-huh.
What?
Well...
Yes. Of course.
Right. I understand.
Okay.
Yeah, that would be perfect.
I'll see you then.
Great. And, uh, listen,
Paige, thank you.
Thank you.
Ah...uh...
Jimmy?
What? What's up?
I, uh...
I just got Mesa Verde back.
Seriously?
Seriously.
Holy shit, that's unbelievable!
I... What happened to HHM?
Uh, Paige didn't go into it.
She just said the filing
didn't go through.
We're gonna meet this afternoon.
Hey, what did I tell you?
Sometimes the good guys win!
Ugh. It sounds like there's
some regulatory issues.
Kevin's still worried that one
lawyer won't be able to handle it.
- You can.
- Yeah...
I'm gonna have to get a paralegal.
Maybe two of them.
And I absolutely
will pay for it out of my end.
No. Come on.
Split it down the middle.
You know what, I need
a Westlaw terminal right away.
I don't even know
who to call to get that done.
- These are high class problems.
- Yeah, but it's a major piece of work, Jimmy.
It's just... This is major.
Hey, Kim, you got this.
All right? So, take a moment.
Breathe. Savor.
You know what? You're right.
Damn right, I'm right.
It's Ernie.
Hi, Ernie. What's up?
Yeah. No, Paige just called me.
Uh-huh.
Did Chuck say why...
So when...
Sure. No time like the present.
Okay.
Thanks.
The Mesa Verde files.
Chuck's ready to turn
them over to me.
Wow!
Really?
That was, uh, quick.
Yeah. I...
I'm gonna go change,
and get over there.
Do you want some help?
That depends. Are you gonna carry
boxes, or are you gonna gloat?
Uh, some from Column A,
some from Column B.
Ground yourself.
Sorry.
Just touch the thing.
What the hell?
This thing doesn't...
- Hey, Jimmy. Hey, Kim.
- Hey, Ernie.
Something's wrong with the lock.
Mr. McGill had me call
a locksmith and change them.
Yeah? Why did he do that?
Hey, Chuck, why'd you
change the locks?
Ernesto, I think we're good.
I'm sure you're needed
back at the office.
- Well, I'll get going then.
- Thanks.
Bye, Jimmy. Bye, Kim.
- Bye, Ernie.
- See you, Ernie.
So, Chuck,
what's the deal with the locks?
Kim, I was hoping to have this
conversation with you, and you alone.
However,
I guess it's time to clear
the air once and for all.
Clear the air about what?
He sabotaged me.
- Buddy, what are you...
- Please.
Don't bother.
You and I both know exactly
what I'm talking about.
I don't.
Yesterday morning was the worst
professional humiliation of my life.
A single transpositional error
cost my client time and money,
and permanently damaged
my reputation.
Then I realized,
it wasn't an error.
Not at all.
A week ago last night,
I was right there, on that couch,
barely conscious.
And Jimmy showed up...
...and he sent Ernesto away.
My brother was gonna
take care of me.
And in the dead of night,
he went through
my Mesa Verde files.
You know what?
We don't have to listen to this.
She does!
You do.
For your own good.
Now, in these files are 13
documents containing the address
of Mesa Verde's proposed branch.
1261 Rosella Drive,
Scottsdale, Arizona.
Jimmy pulled each and every one.
Then left me here,
sweating and delirious,
while he went off to doctor them.
You'd need a photocopier for that.
Where'd you go,
some all night copy shop?
With a little careful cutting
and pasting, he created duplicates,
virtually identical to my originals,
but with one key change.
1261 Rosella Drive
became 1216 Rosella Drive.
This is sounding
like a lot of work.
No one ever accused you
of being lazy.
Every other sin in the book,
but not that one.
And if you're wondering if Jimmy's
up to a little casual forgery,
you should know,
in high school, he had a thriving
business making fake IDs
so his buddies could buy beer.
You're going all the way
back to high school, huh?
Hey, you and Mozart, huh?
You both started young.
He came back here,
and put his new versions in my files.
And then, the next day,
my caring brother took his leave.
He knew that I would use
his modified documents
to write Mesa Verde's submission
to the state regulator.
And so I did.
Over and over,
I typed 1216 instead of 1261.
I remember thinking,
"1216 Rosella Drive,
that's just one year after 1215,
the year the Magna Carta was signed."
Jesus, Chuck. You are unbelievable.
So, you're saying,
if we look in here,
all the addresses will be wrong?
Well, of course you weren't
gonna leave evidence behind.
I'm guessing, yesterday morning
you waited until I left,
then used your key to let yourself
in and return the originals.
No crime is complete
without the cover-up.
Oh, come on.
I did all this, what,
for some business?
He did it for you.
Well, I'm sure you didn't
know anything about it.
I believe he went off on his own,
and did this as some kind
of twisted romantic gesture.
Chuck, I think you need to lie down
with a cold washcloth on your head.
Now that you know,
you have no choice.
This is about a client.
A client who has been defrauded.
As a sworn officer of the court,
as Mesa Verde's attorney of record,
you have no recourse
but to go to Kevin Wachtell
and make a full disclosure.
This whole song and dance is all
about getting his client back.
That's all this is.
Not in the least.
If, knowing the truth,
they still decide to go...
You can't stand the fact
that they chose her over you.
I can't stand the fact my own
brother stabbed me in the back!
I can't stand the fact
that you've deceived
and ruined this fine young woman!
Ruined? What is this, the 1840s?
What are you talking about?
She's not ruined!
Jimmy.
If what you're saying is true,
Jimmy could be
charged with forgery,
fraud, falsifying evidence,
even breaking and entering.
Frankly, I'm sick about this.
But facts are facts.
And what is your evidence?
My evidence...
My evidence is knowing my
brother for his entire life.
Chuck, I think there
is another explanation.
It's a simpler one.
You made a mistake.
I did not.
You're working by lantern light,
squinting over 10-point type
for hour after hour.
Mistakenly changing 1261 to 1216
would be the most natural
thing in the world.
It could certainly happen to me.
I did not make a mistake!
I believe you did.
Look, I understand that you have
great affection for Jimmy.
A great many people do.
But please, open your eyes here!
You made a mistake,
and instead of just facing up to it,
you accuse your brother
of plotting against you.
You come up with this
elaborate scheme...
He's capable of this.
You know he is.
I know he's not perfect.
And I know he cuts corners.
But you're the one who
made him this way.
He idolizes you.
He accepts you.
He takes care of you.
And all he ever wanted
was your love and support.
But all you've ever done
is judge him.
You never believed in him.
You never wanted him to succeed.
And you know what?
I feel sorry for him.
And I feel sorry for you.
Jesus! What?
Kim, what?
Just drive.
All right, line up by class!
Find your buddy!
Let's go.
Come on. Come on.
Plant yourself.
- Here?
- Yeah, right there.
- All right.
- About yea high.
Aim it up at me. Heroic.
Heroic? Good luck with that.
Just frame me up. All right?
Make sure you get the neck, okay?
It's a low angle shot.
- Okay.
- Hey, you know what?
- Let me see.
- Oh, it's just base.
What, am I dying of consumption?
Well, at your age,
you don't want to look too red.
It looks like rosacea.
And what's with all the...
I'm just trying to make it
look like you have a jawline.
I do have a jawline.
You know what?
You stand in for me.
Crouch down. Okay.
Move to your left. The other left.
More. More. Okay. Boom!
That's what I'm talking about.
You got it.
Dude, there's gotta be an
easier way to get this shot.
Not for free.
You wanna be a filmmaker,
grow a pair.
Here we go. Picture's up.
Okay, let's do this.
Last looks.
Rhubarb! Rhubarb! Nine o' clock!
Excuse me.
- Hi, are you in charge here?
- Yes, I am.
And this is school property.
You're just the person
I wanna speak to.
It would be incredibly helpful
if you can get those kids
and that building over there
to just keep it down for a bit.
Just give them a worksheet
or something?
I mean, just two or three minutes,
just for sound.
This is school property, and no one
is allowed here without permission.
Of course not.
You didn't speak to Annette?
Annette?
In the superintendent's office.
- Do you know an Annette downtown?
- I don't think so.
Well, I'm sorry about the mix-up.
We're shooting what's called
an establishing shot.
- Five minutes tops.
- You're not shooting anything
until I'm clear on what's
going on here.
The documentary.
We're making a documentary.
That's... Oh...
I was told there was a display
or a plaque of some kind.
Would you know
where that would be?
Why would we have a plaque?
Because of who went
to school here.
Who went to school here?
Rupert Holmes. That's who
the documentary is about.
I'm sorry, who?
Rupert Holmes. You know.
Rupert Holmes!
The singer songwriter.
You know, uh,
The Pina Colada Song.
I mean, sure you do. I...
♪ If you like pina coladas ♪
♪ And getting caught
in the rain ♪
♪ If you're not into yoga ♪
♪ And you got half a brain ♪
♪ If you like making
love at midnight ♪
♪ In the dunes by the cape ♪
See? Look at her face.
- Rupert Holmes.
- He went to school here?
Yeah. Class of '64.
He still talks about it.
But the school was built in '71.
Hmm. He was a student in the old
building that used to be here.
We're taking a little, what do
you call it, "artistic liberties."
Isn't Rupert Holmes English?
Well, yeah. And that's
some great trivia.
But he spent his formative years
right here in Albuquerque.
I'll tell you what?
Why don't you call Annette down
in the superintendent's office?
And we'll just stay here
till you get official word.
- Well, if you don't mind waiting.
- Not at all.
We don't want to break any rules.
It shouldn't take very long,
I'm sure.
And no promises,
but I'll see what I can do about
getting the kids to quiet down.
Oh, that would be super helpful.
Chop-chop! Magic time!
Come on, let's go.
No last looks!
Just the flag, the flag!
Okay, remember, heroic.
Yeah, you're a hero.
Big, big hero.
Gravitas.
Hey! Hey, hey, hey.
Go.
Dolly, dolly.
Nice.
Hey, Mike.
Hey, Fran.
Are you still serving breakfast?
For you? Sure.
- The usual?
- Uh, that'd be great.
- Thanks.
- Mmm-hmm.
Anything good in the paper?
No. Was there ever
anything good in the paper?
Not too often.
Hey, Fran?
Hmm?
I gotta ask.
Does it ever snow around here?
Sure it does.
This gonna be your first
winter in Albuquerque?
Yeah. I'm out from Philadelphia.
Yeah. It depends on the year.
Hmm.
If you stay around long enough,
you'll have something
to shovel, don't you worry.
That suits me.
I live up in Cedar Crest,
we get plenty.
You can shovel my drive
if you're looking for more.
Just say the word.
Yeah, well...
Miss! Cheque, please.
Yeah.
We gotta talk.
I've got something I need to know.
And I need to know it fast.
- What's that?
- We got hit the other day.
A truck headed south got hijacked,
someone stole a quarter million.
Now Hector's flippin' out,
looking for who did it.
Thing is,
I think it was you.
They left the driver hogtied,
not a mark on him.
Anyone in the game would've capped
him without a second thought.
But this driver,
he's still breathing.
I thought to myself,
"Who's the guy
who'll rip off a couple
hundred thousand in drug money,
and leave a witness?"
"Who's the guy
who won't pull the trigger?"
You.
I'm not here to squeeze you.
You wanna rip off the cartel,
that's your business.
But here's the thing.
I'm picking up that driver.
Hector's orders.
We're gonna see what he knows.
And if he knows you,
that's bad for both of us.
That shouldn't concern you.
But he was in on it, right?
The driver had nothing
to do with it.
- Then who?
- Just me.
You're telling me you did this
without someone on the inside?
Not possible.
How did you know about the truck?
How do you know about the tyres?
All I can tell you is,
you guys aren't half as smart
as you think you are.
So, the driver
doesn't know anything?
Not a thing.
- He hear your voice?
- No.
Right now, Hector's looking
at the competition,
but if he hears the driver
say it was some old gringo...
He didn't hear me.
Saw a guy with a ski mask,
that's it.
And that's for sure?
Yeah.
You'd better be right.
Why wasn't it in the papers?
What?
The truck robbery. The cops
keeping it out of the papers?
The cops?
The cops don't know shit about it.
How's that?
Is that what this is about?
You wanted to put the cops
onto Hector? Why?
You are nothing to him.
He forgot all about you.
I haven't forgotten him.
You put me in the shit,
just 'cause you got it in
for Hector Salamanca?
Listen, you put the cops on him,
you put them on me.
Doing it for the money, I get it.
But this shit, that's insane.
You need to calm yourself down.
And you need to take that
hand out of that pocket.
And just so you know, it's over.
I'm done with your boss.
Whatever.
Why wasn't it in the papers?
Because we cleaned it up.
How's that?
We got lucky.
After you left,
a good Samaritan came along
and said,
"Oh, my God. Oh, my God."
He cut the driver loose.
The driver called us.
We came out, got the truck.
Made it like it never happened.
And that good Samaritan?
Hector shot him in the face.
We buried the guy
out in the desert.
Like I said,
we cleaned it up.
How was your day?
You know. I met with
Paige and Kevin,
interviewed some paralegals.
And, uh, this. What about you?
Finished the commercial.
I don't wanna oversell it,
but I think it might be
the greatest 60 seconds
in the history of television.
Tomorrow morning, uh,
somewhere between 11:18 and 11:35,
stop what you're doing, and tune
into Diagnosis Murder.
I'll make a point of it.
You wanna talk about this?
Not now, not ever.
I'm just gonna say,
you are meant for Mesa Verde,
and they are meant for you.
So, all is right with the world.
Goodnight.
Your brother is one smart lawyer.
The smartest one I know.
I mean, no offence.
He'd make quite an adversary.
You better believe it.
The kind of adversary who'd find even
the smallest crack in your defense.
Going against him,
you'd really want to make sure
you've got all your I's dotted
and your T's crossed.
Nothing for him to find.
Hey, how you doin'?
Be with you in a minute.
Remember me?
Uh...
No.
I got a weird feeling
you do, Lance.
Tonight is a funny night.
For some reason tonight,
I feel like I've got
all the answers.
I'm feeling kinda like, uh...
Like Carnac.
You remember when Johnny
Carson used to do Carnac?
And he'd give the answers
before the questions.
You know, Ed would give
him the envelope, yeah?
And Johnny would hold it up
to his forehead,
and, uh, he'd give the answer.
Like, Leave it to Beaver.
Then Johnny'd tear
open the envelope.
And there's the question.
"What did the dead raccoon
say in his will?"
That ring a bell?
Before your time?
All right, well,
let's cut to the chase.
Um, the guy who just walked
out of here, his name is Ernie.
I'm guessing he showed
you my picture
and asked if I was in here
the other night.
Now he's going to bring
his boss, who is my brother.
And he's gonna ask you
the same question.
"Did you see that guy
the other night?"
Well, the answer is no.
You feel me?
You murder someone?
Nope.
Rob a bank?
No way am I that cool. No.
I... Sometimes,
I go number two, and I don't flush.
But this is just a thing
between brothers.
And we're both lawyers, so...
Right. I mean, that's a
long and boring story.
You don't wanna know.
Is this gonna get me
jammed up with the cops?
My brother might make it
sound like that, but no.
It's just family.
Then I feel you.
Hey, tell me about the cameras?
Oh, uh...
They go to a VCR in the back.
It tapes for 12 hours,
and then records over itself.
Right. So I'm on there now?
How hard would it be to erase?
Hmm...
I don't know.
Could be tricky and expensive.
Like 100 bucks expensive?
Like 200 bucks expensive.
You will go far, my young friend.
Uh... Good evening.
Uh...
Lance, is it?
Yeah.
Lance, I'm Charles McGill.
Uh, my associate, um, spoke with you
earlier, and he showed you this photo.
Um...
On or about the morning
of the 18th,
this person was here in this shop,
is that correct?
Uh...
On or about the...
The 18th, early morning.
No.
Well, I...
I believe you told my
associate that he was here,
and that he made copies.
Yeah, but...
Sorry, no.
Yeah.
That's my guy.
All right, the, uh...
The night of Tuesday the 17th,
leading into early Wednesday,
the early hours of Wednesday,
of the 18th...
Were you in fact here?
Can we establish that?
I mean, I work graveyard.
So, yeah.
Stay strong, Lance.
Was this man here making copies?
Yeah. It's like I said,
I don't think so.
Well, earlier you said
that he was here.
Now you're saying
that he wasn't. Which is it?
Uh, yeah. Well, when that guy
showed me the picture,
I thought maybe.
But now that I'm seeing it again...
Uh, sorry, don't know what to
tell you, guess I was wrong.
Son, listen carefully,
I'm an officer of the court,
investigating a felony.
So, you're a cop?
No. No, I'm not. I'm...
Mr. McGill,
maybe we better get you home.
Ernesto, do not speak to me
as if I were a child. I'm fine.
I am not a police officer.
I am an attorney.
And I have a moral
and legal obligation
to get to the bottom
of this matter.
The bottom of what?
Forgery, fraud,
falsifying evidence.
Breaking and entering.
This guy, is he okay?
There is nothing wrong with me.
Mr. McGill,
maybe we could just take a break.
Ernie, shut up!
You think about the choice
you're making.
I already told you he wasn't here.
What do you want me to say?
I want you to speak the truth.
I know he was here.
I know what he did.
Tell me what you told Ernesto.
Stop trying to change your story.
Excuse me. Sorry.
How do we get this to do 11x14?
No, excuse me,
we are having a conversation here!
You gotta switch it to tray four.
It's easier if I tell you... Look.
Dude... Okay. I... I...
I... I don't want any
problems here. So, just...
Get him out of here,
or I'm gonna call the cops. Okay?
Do not walk away from me.
We are not finished here.
I am done talking to you, man!
Call 9-1-1.
Call 9-1-1. Come on.