Wonderful.
Are the leeks too overpowering?
Not at all.
That's as good as
the one we had in Florence.
Don't humor me.
I'm not.
How was rehearsal?
Did what's her name
behave herself?
She takes the whole
section for granted.
I'm debating
whether to say something.
I think you should, absolutely.
Don't keep it inside.
Ready for the chiffonade?
Yeah, thanks.
And after all, if she's
compromising the work...
Well, it's debatable. I mean, the
Schubert is coming along nicely.
It's more about morale.
Morale can affect quality.
God knows the hoops that
Howard jumps through
just to keep the troops humming.
Well, true.
You deserve a medal for this.
Please. It's no big deal.
Your soy ginger marinade?
Well, I found a citrus
one that looked good,
so I thought I would try that.
Well, anyway, you are a trouper.
And I apologize in advance.
Let's just say he's something
of an acquired taste.
Oh, how bad can he be?
Just in case,
let's have a high sign.
How about the old
Carol Burnett thing?
Oh, where she pulls her earlobe?
Yeah, exactly.
You do this,
and I'll say I have briefs to read,
and we'll get rid of him.
All right,
whatever you want.
- You know why she did that? Carol Burnett?
- Hmm?
It's a great story. It was
a signal to her grandmother,
who raised her, and...
Seriously? He's early.
You're a doll. Hmm.
Holy shit, look at this place!
Hey, Jimmy. Thanks for coming.
Bring it on in here.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, little taste
of home for you.
Had to look all over town
to find a place that had it.
Didn't have time to wrap it.
Well, thanks.
You're good.
Yeah.
I'm lookin' for a place.
Mmm.. mmm.
I've been staying at the Ramada.
Thanks for the help, by the way,
I found a few that I like.
This one place,
the Beachcomber, has a pool.
And since the McGill clan is whiter
than a pack of albino rats,
I figure I'd better
start working on my tan.
So, seriously
considering that option.
I strongly suggest sunscreen.
We're up about 5,000
feet here, you'll fry.
Excellent point. Sunscreen.
Check.
So, a violinist?
Mmm.
And, according to Chuck,
a crazy talented one at that.
Mmm.
I mean, wow.
Well, Chuck is very gracious.
She's being modest.
Rebecca is widely respected
amongst her peers.
Yo-Yo Ma came to our wedding.
That's... Right on, man.
About the wedding, um, I've been
meaning to apologize about that.
I'm truly sorry I wasn't...
No worries.
Please.
So, tell us about your first
week at Hamlin Hamlin & McGill.
It was great!
I mean, they got me
working in the mailroom,
which, you gotta
start somewhere.
I learned how to
use the Xerox machine,
which is
surprisingly complicated.
I mean, press a button, piece of
paper spits out? Not anymore.
- Hmm.
- Thing's practically a computer.
It's like
a goddamn space shuttle.
It's got like,
double sided printing,
automatic stapling,
you know? Hmm.
Met some nice folks.
Guys and gals.
Well, gal, singular, actually.
Learned everyone's name
and I licked a ton of stamps.
My tongue is like hamburger meat.
I mean, seriously.
Unh...
Yeah?
I got...
The thing is raw as hell.
Then I found out there's a sponge for that.
Oops, rookie mistake.
Well, sounds like you had
a very productive week.
Yeah! It was really great.
Hey, guys, um,
I wanna thank you
for having me over.
This is, like, the best meal
I've had in a decade.
I mean, the fish is
perfection. And the...
Risotto.
Thank you. That was very kind.
Well, you're a wonderful chef,
you know?
Aside from being super
talented with the... Yeah.
You got a good one, Chuck.
I mean, lucky, lucky man.
Well, cheers to that.
Oh.
Pardon me.
All right.
What's the difference
between a vacuum cleaner
and a lawyer on a motorcycle?
The vacuum cleaner has
the dirt bag on the inside!
Aha, lawyer jokes.
I've only been in the mailroom a
week, and I've heard maybe 100.
Yeah. It all comes from
a place of affection.
Sure, of course.
What do you get when you cross
The Godfather with a lawyer?
An offer you can't understand.
Very clever.
Never heard that one.
And believe me, I have nothing but the
utmost respect for your profession.
I mean, it's a pillar of...
Oh, why do they bury lawyers
under 20 feet of dirt?
Because deep down,
they're really good people.
What do you call
a lawyer with an IQ of 60?
Your Honor!
What's the difference
between a tick and a lawyer?
Oh, no.
The tick falls off
when you're dead!
Bam! Love that one.
You like that?
Just joking. I want you to know
how seriously I take my job.
I'm grateful for the... Oh.
How many lawyers does it take
to change a light bulb?
Classic set up here.
Three. One to climb the ladder,
one to shake it,
and one to sue
the ladder company!
Comedy gold.
I'm here all night!
More! Go, go.
Okay. Okay, okay, okay.
Dessert, anyone?
We have a homemade blueberry
crumble with vanilla ice cream.
Yeah. Blueberry crumble,
sounds terrific.
I love a fruit based...
Blueberry...
Wait, I think I know one!
Oh, bring it on! Yeah, yeah.
Um, what do lawyers
and sperm have in common?
Oh, that's a... Um.
Three million...
No, wait, um,
one in three million...
Have a chance of
becoming a human being.
Love that one!
Well, that went well,
don't you think?
Sure.
Thanks again.
I don't know what you were
worried about. Jimmy's great.
Yeah. No, he's...
Yeah.
So, what's going on
tomorrow?
Well, I've got the Gernstetter
deposition at 10:00,
back to back partner meetings after lunch.
It shouldn't be a late one.
Thought any more
about what's her name?
It's your reputation,
too, you know?
Well, we start
the Tchaikovsky on Monday,
so, I'll see what kind of mood
she's in when we wrap.
Smart.
What do you call 25 attorneys
buried up to their chins in cement?
Not enough cement.
What?
Oh, oh, oh.
Yeah. Mmm.
Hello, you've reached
the voicemail of Kim Wexler.
Please leave me a message, and I'll
get back to you as soon as I can.
It's me again.
I think I found something that
could help get you out of there.
I'm gonna make things right.
Call me, would you?
Hi. Whoa!
Sorry, I didn't mean
to sneak up on you.
I just thought
everyone was gone.
Nope. I'm here late most nights.
Ah.
By the way,
I noticed in your office,
you threw away a soda can.
You're going through my trash?
No!
I was just dropping off
papers at lunchtime
and I happened to notice
it in your trash can.
I fished it out, so, it's fine.
Office cans are
for recyclable paper.
There's a separate,
big can in the kitchen
for plastic, glass and aluminum.
We take our ecological footprint
pretty seriously here.
Okay, so, the big can
is where I should throw my
empty scotch bottles?
No, I get it.
"Go green."
Good. Was there anything else?
Yeah, one quick thing.
I have the brief you
gave Cliff this morning.
The plaintiff's opposition
to the defendant's motion?
I have a few notes.
I think they're pretty clear,
but it's probably easier if we
just go over them together.
Jesus. Those are Cliff's?
No, they're my notes.
I'd love to go over them now,
if you have a minute.
It looks worse than it is, it's just that
we have a particular house style.
Okay, no offense, but you're a
second year associate, right?
Yep.
And I came in as a fourth year.
That's right.
So, why is a second year
giving notes to a fourth year?
Well, like I said,
I know the house style.
Does Cliff have
you babysitting me?
No! This is just one associate
helping another.
Like here,
the Roman numeral headings?
We use all caps for those.
And you indented them,
which is perfectly fine,
but Cliff likes them centered.
And before I forget,
we put two spaces after a
period on all our documents.
I know it seems
like a minor thing,
but it really looks so much
cleaner on the page.
You went a tad overboard
with the quotations.
It's okay to present a quote from
a controlling legal opinion,
but when you use too many,
it disrupts the flow
of your argument
and it gives the impression
you don't know
how to write
an argument of your own.
And I'm sure you do, so...
You have a tendency to overuse
the words "clearly" and "obviously."
Again, it's a matter
of personal opinion...
I really appreciate this, Erin,
but I was just on my way out.
So, if we could continue this
first thing tomorrow morning.
Well, I was thinking we should
just get 'er done now.
No time like the present!
Sure. Let's roll up our sleeves
and apply a little elbow grease.
Great!
So, I'm gonna get
my favorite pen,
and I will see you momentarily.
You got it.
Uh, miss Wexler?
You can call me "Kim".
Kim, it's 20 to midnight.
Are you asking me
if you can leave?
Guys, I'm not your supervisor.
Don't stick around on my account.
You coming, Kim?
Right behind you. Just
finishing up this last one.
Hey, again. Thanks.
Hey, Gesualdo, could you skip
vacuuming tonight, please?
Hey. Five minutes.
Just give me five minutes.
Here's how we're gonna handle
this travesty of justice.
Wexler v.
Hamlin Hamlin & McGill?
You want me to sue my own firm?
Filing's all typed up,
it's ready to go.
This is not my area of
expertise, all right?
So, first order of business, we get a
great employment law attorney,
show 'em we mean business.
Come on. Hey, look at you!
Okay, you're here.
At midnight, in this glorified cell
block, busting your ass, for what?
It has nothing to do with your
performance. You're being mistreated.
Chuck is punishing
you to get to me.
This is extortion,
pure and simple.
No, that's Howard,
who has an image to uphold.
He did the same thing after
the Kettleman fiasco,
and Chuck was nowhere in sight.
I'm telling you,
Chuck is behind this.
No, you are behind this.
I told you this would happen,
and now I'm paying the price.
I should've known better.
So, now, I'm keeping my head down
and I'm getting through this.
And I'm most
certainly not suing HHM.
Kim...
Even if I won,
who would hire me?
That would be career suicide.
All right.
Then I quit Davis & Main.
What does that accomplish?
It's the only way to
get you out of dutch.
Because this is about Chuck,
whether you wanna believe it or not.
I give him what he wants,
he lets up on you.
Wow. My knight in shining armor.
That is some sacrifice.
Quitting a job
that you've been trying
to tank since day one.
That's not true.
I dig myself out of this hole.
You do your job, Jimmy.
Prove you can go one week.
Hell, one day
without breaking the rules of
the New Mexico Bar Association,
or pissing off your boss.
And don't insult my intelligence
by saying you are
doing any of this for me.
You don't save me.
I save me.
Just please go.
Hey. Is Erin in yet?
Goddamn pixie ninja.
I owe you a big apology.
I have a medical condition.
GERD.
Gastroesophageal reflux disease.
I know, it's a mouthful, right?
It affects the lower
oesophageal sphincter.
I took a risk yesterday at lunch
with some onion rings,
and last night...
Are we doing this, or not?
You bet.
Hey, Jerry,
it's Kim Wexler.
How's things with
the alumni group?
Top 50? Go UNM Law!
Hey, wondering if you've heard
that Santa Fe Place is looking
for new outside counsel?
They should really be considering
Hamlin Hamlin & McGill. We...
Huh. Must've just been a rumor.
Yeah, let's grab a drink soon.
You, too. Okay, bye.
Hey, uh, I remember
you mentioned your
brother worked in
Intel's legal department?
I'm an attorney at
Hamlin Hamlin & McGill,
would you happen
to know if Intel
is happy with their
legal representation?
That's flattering, but I'm seeing
someone at the moment.
So, you know what? Just call the
main number and they'll find me.
Yeah, no,
we had drinks a few days ago,
and she said you
had a friend who...
So, they already settled.
I heard you ended
up at Harvard Law.
Yeah. Yeah, she was my roommate.
Listen, uh, I'm an attorney
at Hamlin Hamlin & McGill.
We're actually known for teaming
with other firms
on large contracts.
Schweikart? Sure. Yeah,
I know them well. It's a great firm.
We met at that
ABA mixer last year?
Yep, bourbon shots. That was me.
Well, congrats on landing
the Honeywell contract.
Huge amount of work.
You, too.
How was your lunch? Good.
What'd you have?
Uh, turkey wrap.
How's the place?
It's great. It's safe,
quiet, they allow dogs.
We can't ask for more than that.
I can't get
Kaylee out of the pool.
By the end of the day,
she's a prune.
I'm glad she's enjoying it.
Hey, I better get her
dinner started soon.
Go to the restaurant.
No, it's too expensive.
I have groceries in the room.
Don't worry about that.
Take her out.
Thanks, Mike.
She misses you.
You think you
might come by later?
No, not yet. I don't want her
to see me looking like this.
How bad was it?
Well, I can tell you, the next car
I get's gonna have airbags.
Well, whenever you
feel you're ready.
It's okay.
It looks worse than it is.
You give Kaylee a kiss for me.
I will.
All right. Bye, darling.
Whoa, whoa, hold up.
What the hell happened to you?
I get it. The first
rule of Fight Club, right?
Let me introduce you.
This is my babysitter, Erin.
Erin, this is my Grandpa, Mike.
Nice to meet you.
Thanks, Tim.
Good seeing you, Jimmy.
Listen, this clerk and I go
way back. We're like this.
But she needs a little finessing,
so can I handle it?
Yeah, sure.
Surprise! Bet you never
thought you'd see me again.
Mmm.. hmm.
I need a summary
judgment hearing
with Michaelis for
Bray v. O'Connell,
and I'm hoping for Thursday
at 10:00, before he...
Don't have it.
Thursday at noon, perhaps?
Nope.
Thursday at 2:00.
Now that's my final...
You're pretty.
Will you be my new mommy?
What are you doing?
What?
That's a bribe!
It's a gift.
That's how it works here.
You grease the wheels of justice.
Give me...
That's not how it works.
You submit the paperwork
and you get a date. Period.
What don't you
understand about finessing?
I apologize for my colleague.
She's new.
Is there any possible way
we can still get Thursday?
I'll give you 2:30 Thursday.
The 14th.
That's next month.
We'll take it.
So, does this go on my
official Stasi report?
I'm not trying to
get you in trouble.
I'm trying to
keep you out of it.
I'm gonna hit the men's room.
The men's room.
Hey, how you doing, Bill?
How am I doing? How are you?
You know, hanging in.
Yeah. Word on the street is you're
over at Davis & Main now.
You lucky son of a bitch.
Oh, you know,
dancing with the devil.
So, how are things
at the District Attorney..
Davis & Main!
Man, that must be sweet.
They give you a car?
Bet they gave you a car.
Yeah. They gave me car.
What kind?
It's a...
No! Don't tell me!
I don't want to know.
I bet it's German. Is it German?
Yeah, it's German.
The cup holder's...
You got a sick office?
I bet you got a sick office.
Pretty sick, it's got
a little fireplace.
Fireplace! I'd kill my
mother for a fireplace.
Hell, I'd kill her for a window.
You have an assistant, right?
Don't tell me. Is she hot?
She's hot, right?
She is a bright
young man named Omar.
Omar.
Hey, you've got
a little something on your...
Uh, yeah. Yeah.
It's vomit. Again.
The worst part? Could've come
from two different defendants.
Scumbags. They're all scumbags.
Oh, my God, where you living?
They put you up?
It's a corporate apartment.
It's just...
Ah, no! Don't tell me.
Christ.
Ah, damn it, I gotta run.
I'm putting away some brain dead
suckwad, who tried to rob a library.
Good seeing you, Bill.
Have a great day.
Yeah. Yeah.
Lucky bastard.
Hello. Hi. This is Kim Wexler.
I did leave a message.
And I was just...
Yes, ma'am.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Hi. This is Kim Wexler.
I was looking for Jennifer Johnson.
No, not his secretary,
I'm an attorney.
Yes I did. I got your number from Chris.
Sure, I will let them know.
Okay. Nope.
Got it. Totally understand.
This is Kim Wexler from
Hamlin Hamlin & McGill.
Actually... Hi. Can I just...
Would you tell him
I'll call him right back?
Okay. Just let me know
when it's a good time.
Got it.
Okay. Thanks for your time.
Hi, Claudia? Kim Wexler.
I'll let him know.
This is Kim Wexler.
I was lookingfor Jillian Coagen.
I met you last
year at the ABA mixer.
For your advice.
Let me get you some.
All right.
Just give me a call. Great.
Kim Wexler.
I did call yesterday.
Okay. I totally get it.
Kim Wexler.
Hey. How are you, Paige?
You did?
That's so nice to hear.
I thought we hit
it off, as well.
Really?
I... I couldn't be
more thrilled.
I mean, the firm and I.
Absolutely.
I'll tell him right now.
I'm sure we can get something
on the books tomorrow.
Day after, at the latest.
Thank you, Paige. Me, too.
Okay, bye.
Yes!
- There she is. Hi.
- Hi.
Paige, so good to see you!
You, too.
Kim, this is Kevin Wachtell,
our CEO.
Kim Wexler.
Great to meet you, Kevin.
And you.
Paige, Kevin, this is Howard Hamlin,
our senior partner.
Pleasure. Likewise.
We're thrilled to
have you folks here.
Kevin, true story.
When I was seven years old,
my very first bank account was at
Mesa Verde, if you can believe it.
I can. Mine was too, back when
my dad ran the place!
Wow. I can remember the cover of
my first passbook.
It was a silhouette of a...
Cowboy.
A cowboy on horseback. Yes.
Standing next to a cactus.
I loved that cowboy.
Far as I was concerned,
I was saving up for that horse.
What the heck else is money good
for when you're seven years old?
So, we have
a little presentation
for you in our conference room.
Along with some snacks and a soy
mocha latte with your name on it.
Oh. This one? She's a keeper.
- Shall we?
- Let's do it.
Well, I think that couldn't
have gone any better.
Pleasure to meet you.
Fantastic. I'll see you soon.
Thanks for setting this up.
I'll talk to you soon.
Lovely to meet you, Paige.
Congratulations.
Right back at you.
I'll circle back with Paige,
get the ball rolling,
start talking strategy,
you know.
Maybe put together a list of staff
associates we can put on this.
I'll put Francis on that.
You've got enough on
your plate in doc review.
Coming.
Huh.
Hey!
Catch you at a bad time?
Not at all. Come in.
I hear clinking.
Does that mean we have
something to celebrate?
We sure do.
What are we drinking to?
Got a juicy one for you.
Mesa Verde!
On retainer.
Oh, even better.
Congratulations. One of
your golf course conquests?
Kim Wexler brought them in.
Fourth year associate snags a
quarter of a million in billings?
She's probably having
a couple drinks herself.
She's out of the doghouse,
I assume?
We'll see.
Huh.
Hmm.
Interstate expansion.
Complex case.
That's two,
maybe, three regulatory
commissions we'll
be dealing with.
Months of work for HHM.
Maybe years.
Good morning, Rudolpho.
Good morning, Mr. McGill.
Oh, sorry!
I didn't know anyone was here.
Just dropping off
some Sandpiper stuff.
You're in early.
More like late.
Well, regardless of the hour,
good to see you here.
Yeah, I'm trying something new,
um, coming in,
working until 9:00.
It's easier before the place opens,
without all the lights,
and the phones ringing.
How about some coffee?
No, thank you.
Would you mind making me some?
I apologize, it's just,
I can't do it myself,
what with the electricity.
Sure.
No sugar. Just a splash of soy milk.
I think we have it.
Kim?
Um, make two cups.
Well, I guess it's
true what they say.
The early bird gets the worm.
Which is good,
if you like worms.
Hmm.
May I ask you a question?
Of course.
Do I have a future at this firm?
We have a lot in common,
you and I.
My brother left
you holding the bag.
If it makes you feel any better,
you're not the first person
to go out on a limb for him.
I made the same mistake
over and over again.
And now Howard has.
And he blames you.
It's a damned mess.
Did Jimmy ever tell you
anything about our father?
Not much, no.
My dad. Our dad...
He was,
well,
the personification of good.
I'm not sure he could even
see sin, in any form.
He was born without the gene.
He ran a little
corner store in Cicero,
cigarettes behind
the counter, penny candy.
Nothing special, but it
kept food on the table.
And the neighborhood loved Dad.
He knew everybody's name,
what was going on in their lives.
This little corner.
He made it better.
I was named after him.
Before that, he had worked for
a lot of people over the years,
and his dream was
to be his own boss.
He put everything he
had into that place.
I was away at college when
he put Jimmy to work there.
Jimmy grew up in that store,
watching our father.
But Dad was not the world's
greatest businessman,
and eventually,
he ran into money troubles.
I had a clerkship at the time,
but I came home to help him get his
books in order, set the ship straight.
Now, I'm no accountant,
but I discovered
$14,000 was just gone.
Vanished over the years.
Turns out Jimmy had pilfered
it in drips and drabs.
Just took it out of the till.
My dad wouldn't hear it.
Nope. Not his Jimmy.
He ended up having to sell.
Six months later, he was dead.
At the funeral, no one
cried harder than Jimmy.
My brother is not a bad person.
He has a good heart.
It's just,
he can't help himself.
And everyone is left
picking up the pieces.
Is there any coffee left?
No. I got it.
I'll talk to Howard. Pour a
little oil on troubled waters.
You're being wasted
down in doc review.
Good job with Mesa Verde.
Mind if I join you?
Hi. What can I get you?
Coffee. Black.
It's coming right up.
Mmm.
He really did a number on you.
Sorry. I know you?
The young man who did that
to you, he's my nephew.
Hothead. Always has been.
Kid thinks he's a boxer.
He should have
shown you respect.
I apologize to you
on behalf of my family.
Apology accepted.
And you know what?
He should go to jail.
Best thing for him. Teach
him respect for his elders.
But not for eight years.
Less. Much less.
You see what I'm getting at?
Not really.
The gun charge, that's eight years
he's going away, maybe 10.
Aggravated assault, the gun,
plus, he got your wallet.
That's right.
I would like for you to tell the
police that the gun was yours.
Would you?
You're both a little
hot under the collar
about whether you
bumped his car or not.
But there was a scuffle
and he got your gun.
My gun?
Your gun from your pocket.
He got it, and that's
how his prints got on it.
Then I would be
subject to the gun charge.
You're an ex-cop.
They'll go easy on you.
So, you're a psychic.
I'll even twist Tuco's ear,
make him apologize.
And he serves for battery.
Nothing else.
I'm looking for the best possible
outcome for everybody.
And for your trouble,
you take home $5,000.
Think about it.