Good night, ladies.
Get home safe.
See you later, Gene.
Good night.
No, no, no, no!
God damn it! No!
Come on.
Hey! Hey!
Somebody!
Hey!
All right. Here he is.
Oh, great. Jimmy, right on time.
Good to see you.
Hello, Howard.
Hey. Hi.
James McGill, Clifford Main.
Just "Jimmy." And it's a pleasure
to meet you, Clifford.
Likewise. We know all about
your work on Sandpiper.
Well, it's a group effort.
I mean, the folks at HHM are
just knockin' it out of the park.
Well, we know the case
wouldn't exist without you.
Absolutely.
Once you get him on your team, you'll
know why I call him "Charlie Hustle."
Jimmy, these are my associates,
Brian Archuleta,
- and Erin Brill.
- Hello.
Nice to meet you both.
It's great to meet you.
I hate to do this,
but could I borrow Ms. Wexler
for a moment?
If you will excuse us?
Pardon me.
What's going on?
I just...
Listen, here's the thing.
If I take this job, does
that mean the two of us...
I mean...
Uh, does it mean...
What? What the hell is this?
If I take this job today,
with Davis and Main,
does that mean
that you and me...
Is this,
is this gonna happen?
Jimmy.
I...
One thing has absolutely
nothing to do with the other.
Nothing at all.
No. Of course not.
Why would it?
Great.
Uh...
Sorry about that.
Listen, I just want to say
thank you, sincerely,
for your interest in me.
It's an honor to be considered,
but at this time...
At this time, um,
I'm gonna have to take
myself out of the running.
Thanks. Thank you, Howard.
Uh, Jimmy?
Well, that was quick.
No charge.
Help me out here.
Did I dream it,
or did I have $1,600,000
on my desk, in cash?
No one on God's green
Earth knew we had it.
We could've split it 50-50.
We could've gone home
with $800,000 each.
Tax-free.
Your point being?
Why didn't we?
I remember you
saying something
about doing the right thing.
You want to know why
I didn't take that money?
Is that what you're asking?
Yeah, that's what
I'm asking.
Me, personally,
I was hired to do a job.
I did it.
That's as far as it goes.
Yeah.
Well, I know what stopped me.
And you know what?
It's never
stopping me again.
Chao cac co, ladies.
Chao cac co.
Mrs. Nguyen, it's a beautiful
day out there.
You should get out of this
place once in a while.
You know, throw a Frisbee,
have some fun.
I have a business to run.
Uh, no.
The business is running you.
Listen to me.
You'll thank me later.
Cucumber water
for customer only.
Hey. It's me.
Hello?
It's me.
I got a new car.
You like it?
We're not taking
that to the meet.
How are we gonna get there?
I'll drive.
My car.
Why?
This business
requires restraint.
That is
the opposite of restraint.
But I like it.
I mean, I'm proud of it.
Good. Then you be proud of it on
your own time, but not with me.
I'm not getting in that.
Okay. Then don't.
Honestly,
you don't really do anything.
I've been paying you
the salary of three people
to just stand behind me.
You know?
And these last few deals...
This Nacho fella,
he's been comin' alone.
I mean, if he
doesn't need backup men,
then,
I mean, why do I need you?
I should just go alone.
I'm throwing...
I'm throwing away money.
Just tossing it
away into the trash.
Look,
you do whatever you want,
but I'm advising you,
do not go to that meet without
someone watching your back.
Yeah, well, of course
you're gonna say that.
I mean, you don't want to be
out of this easy-peasy job.
Well, I'm sorry,
but this is the gravy train,
and it's leaving
the station right now.
So, last chance.
All aboard.
Seriously, last chance.
I'm gonna count to,
say, 10, and then I'm...
All right, then.
Your services are
no longer needed.
Hola.
No old guy?
What, did he break
a hip or something?
I know, right?
Yeah, no, we...
We parted ways.
Yeah, saw things differently.
So... You know how it is.
This is interesting.
Oh, yeah.
You like it?
Can I take a look?
Oh, be my guest. Get in.
Check it out.
Wow.
- Impressive.
- Thank you.
Get in. Feel the leather.
Yeah, it's a H2.
Brand-new, off the line.
Slimmer than the H1,
but longer, more height.
Yeah, it's a honey.
V8 engine, 325 horsepower,
tri-zone climate controls.
So, you can have
a girl in a bikini
and another in a parka, and
they're both gonna be comfortable.
You're running around with
two girls in your SUV?
You'd be really
comfortable, huh?
Oh, yeah. Yes.
I'm gonna count this quick.
Do your thing.
Make sure it's right.
Okey-dokey.
We are good.
Uh, same as before.
Still factory-sealed.
And, as always,
you're welcome to count 'em.
I trust you.
Great. Thank you.
See you next time.
Hello? Yes.
No. Sorry. Uh...
Yes, this is James McGill, but
I'm no longer a lawyer, so...
That's right, not a lawyer.
Bye.
So, this is what
a midlife crisis looks like?
Not midlife crisis.
Clarity.
Midlife clarity.
Clarity? Uh...
Clearly explain to
me why you walked out
on the best job
opportunity of your life.
Get in the pool,
and I'll tell ya.
Get in the pool?
Yeah. Come on.
Just pop in the gift shop
and buy a bathing suit.
Get a one-piece,
nothing fancy.
The water is perfect.
It's 82 degrees.
You can order a drink.
And you got to try this crab dip...
Why are you
acting like this?
I'm not acting like anything.
I just finally
decided to be me.
Everything okay, Mr. Cumpston?
Would you like another drink?
No, I'm good with this.
I'll tell you what,
Mr. Cumpston.
If you really want to talk,
I'll be in the bar.
Not for long.
Hey, Rolando.
Check.
What... What do you mean,
"quit the law"?
I quit it.
Simple as that.
Oh, well, thanks for explaining,
Jimmy. It's super-clear now.
Hey, buddy?
Is that
a misprint right there?
It's got to be, right?
The Zafiro Anejo?
Yeah.
That's correct,
actually, believe it or not.
Holy shit.
A $50 shot of tequila?
Is it worth it?
Apparently.
I mean, it's kind of a
personal choice kind of thing.
Well, I can't die without
trying a $50 shot of tequila,
so, two,  dos, neat.
And we can charge that
to the room, can't we?
No, we can't.
We...
I am paying.
And he will be having a shot
of your well brand,
and I'll have
a glass of your house red.
We have a Cabernet,
a Pinot, and a Syrah.
Whatever. Dealer's choice.
Something with alcohol.
You got it.
Jimmy.
Did something
happen in Cicero?
Why did something
have to happen in Cicero?
Because when I talked to you
about Davis and Main,
you were ready
to take the job.
Now you're back, and you're
suddenly quitting the law,
cheating hotels out
of expensive liquor,
wearing a weird pinkie ring?
What,
are you in the Mafia now?
Asking if we have a future.
I mean,
where did that come from?
I don't know. I just...
Well, Cicero has
nothing to do with it.
It's my whole life.
Well, my life since Chuck mad
me come to Albuquerque.
Ever since I got here, all I've done
is try to make Chuck happy,
bend over
backwards to please Chuck.
Chuck, Chuck, Chuck.
Well, no more.
You quitting the law, isn't that
exactly what Chuck wants?
Who cares?
This is for me, okay?
I got into the law
for all the wrong reasons.
I'm trusting my instincts.
I think that my talents
are better spent elsewhere.
Where? Floating in
somebody else's pool?
Jimmy, you're a great lawyer.
Why give that up?
I'm not saying it
didn't have its moments,
but the stuff I
liked about it,
selling people,
convincing people,
I don't have to be
a lawyer to do that.
Besides, people tell
me how they see me,
and it's not as a lawyer.
All right.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Let me know if I can get you
guys anything else, okay?
Bobby,
what up, brother man?
Thanks.
Short it.
Short it. Short that shit.
That stock is useless.
It's got no legs.
It's like a circus
freak minus the fun.
And that one's even worse.
Who's giving you these?
Please do me a favor.
Take a pillow,
put it over
that stock's face
until you hear
the deathbed queef.
Okay, so...
If you're not gonna be
a lawyer, then what?
Float around and wait for your
Sandpiper money to roll in?
No.
That could take years.
Sandpiper has no
bearing on this at all.
Okay, then,
what's the plan?
To be open to the universe.
Okay, so no plan.
Just walk the Earth, like Jules
at the end of Pulp Fiction?
Look, whatever
the universe presents,
whatever opportunity arises,
I will take it.
Whatever opportunity?
Yeah.
Wasn't Davis and Main
an opportunity?
It's a great opportunity,
and you're walking away from it.
Look, shouldn't you at least try
the job before you say no?
And waste everyone's time,
including my own?
Kim, I appreciate your concern,
but it's not for me.
I don't want it.
Jimmy, do you remember how
long you studied for that bar?
How hard you worked?
Yeah.
All that effort, you're just
gonna toss it away?
That's the sunk cost fallacy.
Wait, the what?
The fallacy of sunk cost.
It's what gamblers do.
They throw good
money after bad
thinking they can
turn their luck around.
It's like, "I've already spent this
much money or time, whatever.
"I got to keep going."
No, there's no reward
at the end of this game.
You are making a mistake.
I know you're
making a mistake.
I've been doing the right thing
for all these years now,
and where has it gotten me?
Nowhere.
I'm sorry. I don't...
It's not my thing.
I don't get it.
I just don't get it.
It's what's right for me.
Donkey balls.
Pure donkey balls, dude.
Wall Street's for suckers.
Who needs that aggravation?
If the Oracle doesn't have to live
there, then I sure as hell don't.
I can make
a million-dollar stock trade
on my laptop
sitting on a toilet.
Like Midas, shitting gold
bricks on my throne.
That's why Speigelman and
Deitch want my business so bad.
I'm a golden God.
Look,
of course I remember that.
Who forgets
a thing like that?
That fart had the anger of a
repressed minority community.
You fart like that
in someone's face,
you're gonna give
them pink eye for life.
Good convo, bro.
Till next time, brother man.
Come with me.
What?
Just come on. Trust me.
What are you gonna do?
You want to understand
what I'm talking about?
Follow my lead.
Hey, buddy,
could you settle a bet for us?
A what?
Sorry.
I don't want to make it sound like I
was eavesdropping, but I kind of was.
We heard you
talking about stocks.
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah, so, a question,
if you could settle a debate
between me and my sister.
All right. You know what? We probably
shouldn't even bother this man.
We wouldn't normally do this, right?
But we need an expert.
This guy sounds like
he knows his stuff.
Yeah, go.
Okay. Here's the question.
When it comes to the
stock market, is there, like,
a financial limit to how much
a person's allowed to invest?
A limit?
No.
No limit.
Knew it.
Oh, even if it's
an inheritance?
You know, with, like, inheritance
taxes and whatnot?
No. Same.
That's, oh, fantastic.
Thank you, buddy.
See? No limit.
Told you we
could invest it all.
And it's a smart move, too.
Sticking it all in the bank?
No.
Um, yeah.
You can invest
all your money.
Just make sure
you diversify.
Yeah. Diversify.
That's... We got to...
Hey, what do you mean,
"diversify"?
Well, diversify is...
You know that saying,
"Don't put all your eggs in
one basket," right?
Same principle.
No, it makes complete sense.
Thank you.
Now, if I had an idea of the money
we're talking about, ballpark,
I could give you examples
of smart diversification.
Yeah, um...
Look, an uncle on our father's side
recently passed,
and he left us somewhere
in the neighborhood
of $1.4 million.
And I don't mean
to be greedy,
but I think if we
invest it smart now,
we could double it,
triple it,
we could quadruple
the whole inheritance, right?
In my opinion?
Fortune favors
the bold, man.
Now, if you guys are free
to join me for a drink,
I can give you a quick consult.
That's all right.
We were gonna do
it ourselves through
one of those online
brokerage websites.
We're just gonna
pick a classic, like,
I think they're
called blue-chip stocks?
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
you can totally do it yourself.
Shoot for the tried
and true.
'Course, you might be putting your
cash in the Hindenburg,
the Andrea Doria,
Corky Romano.Right?
They all seemed rock-solid
beforehand, but then...
Yeah, not good.
Not good, yeah.
So, how do you know?
Well, that's where
someone like myself comes in.
Proven track record
as a wealth manager.
I take calculated
but aggressive risks
'cause I want to
catch lightning.
And I do.
Practically
a money-printing machine.
That sounds good.
A money-printing machine.
Listen, there's
a little booth over here.
There's some privacy.
We can talk.
No obligations. We can just
rap about this a little bit.
Yeah, I guess.
Yeah?
What do you say, sis?
Can we just talk?
Electric slide on
in there.
And we'll just
rap a little bit.
It's no...
My name's Ken, by the way.
Uh, Viktor, with a "K."
Cool. Viktor with a "K."
And this lovely lady is?
It's Giselle.
Giselle Saint Claire.
Ah, lovely.
Please, sit.
I won't bite.
So, Viktor with a "K"
and Giselle... Exotic names.
They're Dutch.
Well, Boer,
to be precise.
Our father's side of the
family is from South Africa,
which is where Uncle
Humphrey passed away.
Oh, South Africa.
They grow them beautiful down
there, right? Charlize Theron.
And you.
Oh, well...
I've never actually been,
but hope to go someday.
Tell you what, by the time
I'm done with you two,
you might be taking
your own private jet.
Nice.
Excuse me. Hi.
Uh, we are sitting here now,
so we could use a wine list,
if you get a chance...
Hey, are you a tequila fan?
Yes.
You down for that?
You ever try Zafiro Anejo?
No, I have not,
but I'm down for whatever.
Three of
whatever she just said.
You got it.
All right.
So, stock market.
A great investment.
And you're picking
the right time to jump in.
Why do you listen to me?
I'm an idiot.
And talks about his cars,
talks about...
How many cars did he have?
I don't think...
It doesn't make sense.
That's it, Ken.
Oh, yeah.
Compliments of the bartender.
She thought you
might want a souvenir.
Oh, my God. Did we drink
the entire bottle?
Not yet, we didn't.
Hey, hey, cheers.
I think we're
ready for the check.
Oh!
Now, really,
it's the smart way to go.
But, so, to be clear,
you take the money directly
from our account and invest it.
Diversify.
Diversify it.
And then all the dividends
and all the profits
and the what-have-you
comes back into our account.
Boom, absolutely.
And you'll get
a detailed statement
showing you how much
your money is growing,
biggest bulls of the month,
et cetera.
Ken, buddy,
let's do this.
Great.
Right there, Viktor with a "K,"
and, Giselle, you are next.
This is so exciting.
Mmm-hmm.
Folks, it's been
a pleasure.
Oops, I got that.
Can't let you do it, son.
Wait. What?
Ken, you are the greatest.
- Thank you.
- No problemo.
Hey, this will be the best
decision you'll ever make.
Oh, I believe it.
All right, well, we should
get out of your hair.
Yeah.
Wait, wait.
This is for you. Now,
that's got all my contact info.
Call me anytime with
questions or anything at all.
Ken.
Bye.
Call me, guys.
Try and stop us.
Wow.
Just wow.
Hey.
What...
Is this right?
Yes, sir, it is.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Zafiro Anejo.
Shh. He's gonna come out.
Oh, no.
- I didn't read the fine print.
- Wait.
Yeah.
Holy crap.
I can't...
Can I borrow that
when you're done?
No, that's gross.
How is it gross? Our germs
have already intermingled.
It's my toothbrush.
It's different.
Why is it different?
Because.
You know,
gums bleed, and there's...
There's cold sores,
all sorts of food and...
Come on.
What? No.
I'll do it right now.
I don't care.
I need to brush my teeth.
I don't have an extra.
It's not my problem.
That's fine.
I got this.
Good. I'm fine with this.
Yeah, me, too.
Wait till you see
what I floss with.
That's a keeper.
Thank you,
Viktor with a "K."
Hey, wouldn't it be great if we
could do that every night?
Yes, it would.
But we can't.
I know, yeah.
But I'm just saying,
if we could, it would be great.
But I know we can't.
Oh, crap.
I can't be late today.
Howard is doling
out assignments,
and the last one
through the door
could get stuck in doc review.
You got somewhere to go?
Yeah. Uh, yeah,
I got somewhere.
You good?
Yeah. All good.
Daniel Wormald? I'm Officer Baker.
This is Officer Saxton.
Yeah, please. Come on in.
Come in. It's over here.
See what they did?
I mean, all gone.
All of them, just...
Uh... What's all gone?
I have.. I had a baseball
card collection.
A major collection,
all stolen.
Oh, sorry to hear that.
Was it common knowledge
that you have baseball cards?
No, not really.
So, nobody in particular
you can think of wanted 'em?
No. Not that I...
No.
How'd they get in?
Uh, the back door over here.
It was open when I
came home for lunch.
I mean, it was locked,
but they must have
jimmied it open or something.
Uh-huh.
At what time
you figure this happened?
I left for work at 8:15,
came home for lunch at 12:30,
and called you immediately.
Was anything else taken?
Cash, a fair bit, uh...
How much cash?
Uh, I don't know.
Let's focus on
what's important here.
You know, all I really care
about are my baseball cards.
You know,
I have a Topps Mickey Mantle
rookie card
that's irreplaceable.
It's a mint,
60/40, 90/10 on the reverse.
I can go on.
All my cards are
in top-loaders,
but if they're taken out
and exposed to the elements,
I mean,
or creased, God forbid.
I mean, you're
looking at a nine-point
downgrade in
a matter of seconds.
I understand
the first 48 hours
are the most important
in investigations like this.
So, the more time passes,
I mean, the less likely
we are of a recovery.
So, time is of
the essence here, guys.
Well, we're gonna help you
out the best we can, Mr. Wormald.
Good.
Well, they really tossed this place.
I mean, are you sure they weren't
looking for anything else?
Like what?
I don't know.
Just wondering your thoughts.
I assume more baseball cards.
Did you have
more baseball cards
than the ones you keep
locked in that case here?
Yes, in back. Thousands.
But these were
the crown jewels over here.
The all-star lineup.
Right.
Hmm.
What?
Just trying to make sense of it.
What's to make sense of?
I mean, isn't it as
simple as the perp
was looking for
more baseball cards?
Or hopped up on
speed or whatever
and went nuts
with the vandalism?
Yeah. I mean,
that could be.
Yeah.
Pretty sweet Hummer
parked in the driveway.
That yours?
Yeah, that's mine.
Uh, it's a lease.
Got a great deal on it.
It's very sweet.
They say Arnold Schwarzenegger
is the reason that Hummers exist.
I don't know how,
but that's what they say.
No kidding.
Yeah.
Uh...
What kind of work do you do,
Mr. Wormald?
Uh, I work IT for
a pharmaceutical company.
Wow, computers.
God, I should've
gotten into computers.
I'd have that same Hummer.
Yeah, right.
Look, guys,
I'm glad you like my car.
But I think
we're lookin' through
the wrong end of
the telescope here.
The priority is
my baseball cards.
Of course.
Yes, now, I have a detailed
manifest of my entire collection.
And asterisks next to
the high-ticket items.
So, it's clear which ones
they're gonna try to fence first.
'Cause they're super,
super valuable.
So, you're gonna want to get this list
out to pawnshops, uh, collectors.
Question anyone who's done any
sort of crime like this in the past.
The usual suspects.
Uh, can I get you the list so
you can start investigating?
Yeah, you... Yeah, if you
could get us that list...
Okay, I'll print it out.
Hank Aaron, mint.
God, my signed Derek Jeter.
Willie Mays, O-Pee-Chee.
Got to breathe.
Just keep breathing.
Keep breathing.
Okay.
I know, right?
Left the TV.
Uh-huh.
Left the computer.
Right.
Uh...
There's something
wrong with this picture.
Hey, it's me.
Another perfect day
in paradise out here.
I'm in the pool.
Okay, call me.
Hi. How are you?
Hey, babe.
Did you get lunch?
I did.
I think I'm burning up back here.
Really? Well, you're just in luck.
- Look what I have.
- Oh, great.
Oh, yeah, you're all red
back here. Yeah.
That feels good, babe.
I told you not to spend
so much time in the sun.
You don't listen.
Yeah, it's me again.
Listen, as I speak,
not 25 feet away from me,
I'm looking at the mark.
Think Thurston Howell III
if he shacked up with Ginger.
He's dripping in Gucci.
It's like I'm at the watering hole
and I'm watching the fattest,
slowest water buffalo
expose his neck to me.
And I'm the lioness
ready to strike.
Come, Kim, join me.
Join the pride.
Oh, I said "lioness" because it's
the females who do all the hunting.
Uh, I just wanted to be species-accurate,
irrespective of my own sex.
It's a National
Geographic thing.
Anyway...
Get out here.
Bye.
Santa Fe, New Mexico.
I need the number of a law firm.
Davis and Main.
Yeah, you can connect me.
There are a few options
on the company cars.
We can arrange a test drive
whenever you'd like.
Company car. Wow.
And there's a service
that will deliver it
right to you,
wherever you want.
And if you find
you're not happy with it,
it's not a big
deal to change it out.
That sounds really...
Yeah.
This is uh, interesting.
Oh, if...
If this isn't to
your taste,
we have a collection of art in-house
you can choose from.
Anytime you're ready,
I can put together some samples
for you to review.
I... No, I like this.
Good. Well, any other
needs you have,
I'm here to help.
Office supplies,
dietary needs...
Anything special you want
stocked in the fridge?
Uh, maybe a humidifier?
Gets kind of dry in here.
Omar, I'm pretty
low-maintenance.
Sure.
Well, if there's anything
you need,
I'm right outside the door.
Great.
If I think of anything.
Good.
Hey, do you think...
Uh, I'm just looking at this.
Do we get a choice of desks?
What were you thinking?
Uh... Is it possible...
Um...
Can we do a cocobolo?
Cocobolo desk?
Absolutely.
I'll get right on that.