Ahead.
Turn to the left.
Step around
the back of the truck.
Okay.
Here you go.
You know,
I was willing to take you
to a more
high-end establishment.
This requires
a proper celebration,
so don't think
that this counts.
This is perfect.
Besides,
we're pinching pennies now.
When we have a steady
revenue stream,
make the drive up to
Geronimo every night.
Till then...
Yes, that.
Let's make that happen.
Okay,
here's what you got to do.
Type up your resignation
letter, now, I mean, tonight.
Tonight? Yeah.
Well, I mean, finish your
hot dog first, but...
No, you put that letter
into Howard's office tonight.
It's on his premises. You've
officially given notice.
Tomorrow morning, while he's
still out on the back nine,
chasing his balls,
you call Mesa Verde
and your other clients,
you bring them along, you
get to them before he does!
No. What, "no"?
You gotta act now.
Listen, you do this "the
right way", you wait,
you tell Howard to his face,
he'll sink his dirty hooks
into Mesa Verde
before you get the words "I
quit" out of your mouth.
Okay, Jimmy,
I appreciate the advice.
But the whole point of this
is for you to be your kind of
lawyer, and me to be mine.
I need to find a way to do
this that's right for me.
Hey, Kim. Can we make this quick?
I'm kind of swamped right now.
Um, sure.
Thanks for meeting with me.
I only need a few minutes.
Great. What's up?
Howard, could we
do this in your office?
Please?
Again, thanks for
taking the time.
You can just go ahead
and rip off the Band-Aid.
I have a pretty good idea
why you're here.
So, you're going
with Schweikart & Cokely.
I'm sorry? I heard.
Through the grapevine.
I'm not going to another firm.
I'm starting my own.
I figured I'd try giving it a
go as a solo practitioner.
Well, I...
Wow.
I realized it was something
I needed to do.
The week Jimmy exits Davis &
Main, you decide to leave us?
That can't just
be happenstance.
It's not.
We're gonna be
sharing expenses.
One office, but two
separate practices.
Smart. On several counts.
Howard.
I want you to know that I
appreciate my time here.
I'm grateful for everything you
and the firm have done for me.
Especially the financial
help with my schooling.
And I'm ready to write a check
for the remainder of the loan.
I just need Accounting
to get me that figure.
No need. Our gift to you.
I don't know what to say. Um...
Thank you.
You earned it.
Tell you the truth,
I'm kind of envious.
Really? Why?
Something about a fresh start.
Back in the day,
right out of law school,
I thought long and hard about
hanging up my own shingle.
Yeah? Yeah.
I was ready to
take on the world.
Make a difference.
Dad talked me out of it.
Wanted me to
join the ranks here.
Throw another "H"
in the firm's logo.
Things work out the way
they're supposed to, I guess.
Kim, I want you to know
that I always pushed you harder
because I knew that I could
expect more from you.
Good luck to you.
Thank you.
Julie, get me
Kevin Wachtell at Mesa Verde.
And cancel everything
I have lined up this morning.
Calling now.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
Hi, Paige! It's Kim. Yeah, hi.
Just checking that we're still
on for lunch on Monday?
Great. And Kevin, too?
Good. Well, before we meet,
there's some news
you need to know about.
I am not the safe choice. The
safe choice for you would be HHM.
I believe, however,
that I am the right choice.
Why?
That suit you're wearing,
did you buy it off the rack?
Please don't tell me it
looks like I did.
If it did,
I wouldn't have asked.
So, why do you prefer
a tailor-made suit?
Because it fits
you and you alone.
Because each and every stitch was
fretted over with you in mind.
Either you fit the jacket,
or the jacket fits you.
What if I want a whole
warehouse full of suits?
That's a hell of
a lot of sewing.
How's one single tailor
gonna get that job done?
I know your
bank's needs in regard
to this expansion,
inside and out.
Having Mesa Verde
as my sole client
will take up the entirety
of my attention, to be sure.
But if this were
beyond my abilities,
I wouldn't be
throwing my hat in the ring.
I would not waste your time.
Or mine.
Hey, Kim,
we're in here.
Perfect timing. I was
just getting the tour.
Kim, this is Steve. Hi.
Steve's the agent
for the place.
Hi. Kim. Nice to meet you.
Hi, Kim.
Everything okay?
Wow.
What do you think?
I...
I think it's a...
It's a dentist's office.
Two offices for two dentists.
Each the exact same size,
with a mirrored layout.
Here. The other one
is the next door over,
right beside this one.
Right here.
But they share one lobby,
one reception area.
So, egalitarian as hell.
Not to mention efficient!
Also, soundproofed walls.
What with the drilling
and the pain and the whatnot.
And the location,
I mean, holy crap!
I think this is the place.
Kim?
Yeah, it's great.
Soundproofing.
Hey, Steve, would you
mind if we just...
Please, I'll step outside
and make some phone calls.
You all take all
the time you need.
Bad lunch?
Mesa Verde said no?
Okay. I'm getting
mixed signals here.
Is this a good...
Jimmy, I got it!
You got Mesa Verde? Yes!
I mean, there's nothing
in writing yet,
but the lunch went...
It kicked ass!
It was a little touch-and-go
there for a moment, I'll admit.
But Paige pitched in
and she really talked me up,
and then once
that door cracked open...
High-five! Fantastic.
I had an answer for every
question, every concern!
And I did not badmouth HHM,
not at all, but I was, like,
"Enthusiasm", you know?
And "Personal service",
because that's got to count
for something.
Shit, yeah, that counts!
Exactly! So...
I mean, 'cause, like, why were they
even at HHM in the first place?
Me! So...
And then when we walked
out of the restaurant,
when Kevin wasn't looking,
Paige gives me a thumbs-up.
But not the regular thumbs-up,
the double thumbs-up.
Two. Double-barrel.
Boom, boom. Just like that!
I knew it.
I knew you could do it!
It was just...
God! It was perfect.
What?
I just... I love
seeing you like this.
So, are we gonna
keep these chairs?
Does that mean you
like this office?
Let's do it.
Hell yeah, let's do it!
Ernesto, the door's open!
As always.
Ernesto?
It's me, Chuck.
Hey, Howard.
Is Ernesto with you?
No, it's just me.
Well, I expected a round
of documents an hour ago.
You know we got
a filing coming up.
I know, Chuck.
It's very possible...
It's likely that
we're losing Mesa Verde.
Losing them? We just got them.
Why? Where are they going?
They're going with Kim Wexler.
She left the firm.
Kim left?
Howard...
Well...
Where's she going?
Is it Rich Schweikart?
Or did Reeves
and Green get her?
No. Not another firm. She's
going into private practice.
What?
Well, that's completely...
How is she going
out on her own?
Why is she going
Well, the why is the why.
The how is that she's
pooling her resources.
With Jimmy.
Kim and my brother.
Partners at law.
He's Svengali.
The man is Svengali.
At any rate,
back to Mesa Verde.
I'm gonna try
one last Hail Mary.
Chuck? Mesa Verde.
Yes. Listening.
I managed to get a meeting
with Kevin Wachtell.
He's coming in this afternoon.
But compliance law
is not my strong suit.
So, if you have any details,
any arguments,
bullet point them for me now,
because I've got about an hour
before I have to get back.
Chuck.
I really need your help here.
Chuck?
Are you okay?
I'm going to that meeting.
Chuck.
I don't know if
that's a good idea.
I can do it!
Force of will. And I've
been getting better.
I know you have, but the message
that we want to send...
I know the message!
That we appear professional
and not crazy!
I'm going to the meeting,
and the lights stay on.
Everyone keeps their phones.
Everything stays, for lack
of a better word, "normal".
I will make it through.
Yeah.
They're here.
Okay.
Hello, everyone.
Sorry I was delayed.
Not at all. We just sat down.
Kevin Wachtell, Paige Novick,
this is Charles McGill.
Chuck. Kevin. Paige.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you both
for coming.
And don't worry, I'm not here
to extol the virtues of HHM.
I'm guessing you've
already had to suffer
through Howard's hard-sell
first time around,
so, you've done your time,
as far as I'm concerned.
What hard-sell? It was enthusiasm!
I gave them cookies!
Cookies were good, as I recall.
No, I am here
to put your minds at ease.
Kim Wexler is indeed the right
choice to handle Mesa Verde.
She's the obvious choice.
She's young, she's brilliant,
she's going places.
Let's face it, Howard.
She's the future.
Two old guys like us?
We're the past.
Well, that's a sad thought.
Sad, but true.
Banking law
needs to be exciting!
It needs the next generation
to come along
and give it a big old kick
in the seat of the pants!
Really wake it up! Let me
tell you how boring I am.
I read FEC and ISO reports
for entertainment.
He does. I can attest to that.
Well,
I try to stay up on things.
The rules are
changing all the time.
With everything that's happened
with Enron and WorldCom,
the government
is extra vigilant.
These days, the penalties for
even the most honest of errors
can be devastating.
You need a sharp, young eye
to catch that stuff.
I mean, when you've specialized
in this kind of work
for decades on end,
you tend to get kind of...
Stale. Stale. You get stale.
You forget things like,
I don't know, the
Community Reinvestment Act.
Any bank such as Mesa Verde
looking to open a de novo branch
is definitely
going to need to show
a healthy portfolio
of CRA compliance.
Duh.  Obviously.
You guys have all that
covered, I'm sure.
Riegle-Neal Interstate Banking
and Branching Efficiency Act.
There's another mouthful.
Boring!
Still, if you were
to run afoul of it,
it could hold you up
in court for years.
And by the way,
if that were to happen to you folks,
as you go forward without us,
which it will not,
um, Howard has contacts at the Fed
who could help sort things out.
One or two. -
Then there's the SEC's interpretation
of Section 302 of Sarbox.
Blah, blah, blah.
Well, navigating that
correctly could mean savings
of several hundred
thousand dollars.
They know that, Howard.
I apologize.
When you reach
your golden years,
you tend to get
a little long-winded.
Ramble on and on about details.
My point being, your bank
is in excellent hands.
Look, I take your point. I do.
But I have to say, I have complete
confidence in Ms. Wexler.
You should.
She was part of our team.
She learned from us.
You won't find
better than Kim Wexler.
But no matter how talented
one individual may be,
the needs of Mesa Verde
are too big to handle alone.
I wouldn't handle
your coming expansion alone.
Which is why you should
consider, once again,
enlisting a team
of professionals.
Glad we did this.
Anytime.
We are there for you,
day and night.
Lovely to meet you, Paige.
And you. Thank you.
Talk soon, gentlemen.
Chuck, that...
That was amazing!
Fantastic. Truly...
Whoa. Chuck?
Get me home.
Ernie! Hang on.
Again, we want to
thank you for
accommodating
the Major like this.
You kidding? It's an honor.
For a war hero, I think we can
bend the rules a wee bit.
Well, we really
appreciate it.
Major Talbott's grandsons are
only in town for one more day,
so it's great they get to share
this experience with him.
You guys are in
for a real treat.
You excited?
Yeah, yeah, excited.
So, these are your boys?
No, no,
I'm the family attorney.
I just help when I can,
so I called you.
Well, I am glad
to be of service.
And here she is.
Gentlemen, meet  FIFI.
The world's last airworthy
B-29 Superfortress.
She's based in Texas, but
she's here for a quick visit.
Just kind of a morale builder
for the airmen.
The crew's on lunch,
unfortunately.
Otherwise, I was gonna see
about showing you inside.
Isn't she a beauty, Fudge? Just
like the one you used to fly!
Yep.
Major Theodore "Fudge" Talbott.
His mom used to mail him care
packages of fudge during the war,
and he'd share them
with his friends, so...
That's the story. Right, guys?
Yes.
Well, sir, this certainly must
bring back some memories for you.
Too many to count, he says.
I've got to say, Major Talbott.
It's a privilege. So, thank
you for your service.
He says "You're welcome."
Um...
Boy, I envy you guys.
I mean, the stories
you must have heard.
You remember any good ones?
Bombing stuff. Bombing stuff.
That's... Like...
Like the war.
Did he fly over the Hump or
did he take off out of India?
I think...
You doing okay?
You need some water?
Yes. Yes, sir.
Nuts, I forgot his water.
Hey.
I can run back to the office,
get him a bottle.
You could?
Fudge, the captain's gonna
run back to his office.
Get you some water. Okay, sir?
All right. That's great.
And there's no rush.
He's gonna be fine.
I'll be back ASAP.
Up. Up.
I thought I told you
not to say anything.
Go stand by the front.
The nose! Whatever.
Where the hell did
you find this guy?
You couldn't get
a real war hero?
Yeah, like they grow on trees!
This guy owes me.
I defended him a while back
when he couldn't pay.
Defended him for what?
What, you wanna be a lawyer
when you grow up?
Just fix the...
Public masturbation.
Total bullshit!
All right.
Keep your voice down.
You do not possess
the power of speech.
Okay, let's go!
Let's go! Chop-chop!
All right, hands on your hips.
All right. Looking strong,
looking proud. All right.
See the bomber, okay?
The bomber's the main point,
so see it.
I see the freaking bomber.
Couldn't you just pop the dude
in front of a flag?
Why'd we have to come here?
Production value. Showmanship!
You rolling? Yeah, rolling!
Okay, start the dolly.
Action!
You're part of
the greatest generation!
You fought the Nazis!
Fought the Japanese.
Fought Japanese.
I fought the Japanese.
This machine was used in the
Pacific where the Japanese are.
Why don't you shut up and
learn to take some direction?
Japanese.
All right, fine.
You fought all
the dirty Axis Powers.
Your band of brothers came
together and you saved the world!
You're heroic!
Not that heroic. Just throw
it away a little more.
Okay, good.
You've got red, white, and blue
coursing through your veins.
Look up! Picture a
bald eagle, soaring!
Shit.
Okay, just keep rolling.
Tights, wides, just get me
some good angles.
All right, back to one.
Back to one.
Fudge.
Fudge. Right here. Fudge.
What is it, Ernie?
Jimmy, man, I'm at
your brother's and he's bad.
Bad, how bad?
He's... I don't know. Bad. Shaking.
I've never seen him like this.
He keeps telling me
not to call a doctor.
Let me guess. He's been
going in to the office?
Yeah, more and more. He had
a big meeting there today.
Okay, here's what you're gonna do.
Wrap him in a space blanket.
He's already under one.
Wrap him in a second one.
Make him some tea, or just
better, heat some chicken broth.
Just let it simmer,
don't make it boil.
That's it? No doctor?
That's it. No doctor. He's
just got to ride this out.
Chuck'll be fine.
Shit, I gotta go.
Rhubarb! Rhubarb!
Idiots, that's the signal!
Get him in the chair!
Where's the air hose?
Stick it in your nose.
Come on.
Sir!
Hey! This is not a problem.
Do you mind if the guys and I
took a picture with you?
It would mean a lot to us.
Yeah, pictures.
He loves pictures.
Here. Give me the camera.
Yeah, here's your water.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Here. All right!
Let's scoot you in.
Swing ya around.
Okay. Everybody line up!
Smile!
Cheese!
You ready to sign?
Let's do this!
What?
I lost Mesa Verde.
I had him.
I thought I had him.
So, what happened?
They're sticking with HHM.
Paige said they went over there
this afternoon for some kind of
courtesy meeting,
or so she thought.
And Kevin got his head turned.
By Howard?
No.
Chuck.
Jimmy, I have to ask...
Are you still up
for doing this?
What, you mean
getting the office?
All of it. I think...
Maybe we need to slow down
and really, you know,
think about this.
Wait. Whoa. Nothing's changed.
Nothing's changed?
We're about to sign
a very expensive lease
after a very
sizable chunk of income
just went flying
out the window.
That's why we're a team.
Something like this happens,
you're there to help me,
I'm there to help you.
Hey. There will be
other Mesa Verdes.
So, you still want to do this?
Jimmy.
I did everything you said, but
he's not getting any better.
You did good, Ernie.
Thanks. Why don't you go
home and get some sleep.
I'll take over.
He told me he
wanted me to stay.
It's okay. I'm here now.
And next time you see Howard,
tell him you need a raise.
A big one.
Chuck, buddy?
How you feeling?
Hey, how's it going?
I need an X-Acto knife,
a ruler, wood, please.
Hammermill Premium paper, 20lb,
one ream, and a glue stick.
And point me to
your best copier.
Best copier? Yeah, best copier.
Come on,  di di mau!
♪ Been a strange old week With the stuff
you didn't do and the people that you meet
♪ And digging up the words
like pulling teeth
♪ Got a face, a number
♪ And a name
that she goes under
♪ I guess there's plenty worse
places to be
♪ So why don't you do it?
♪ Yeah, why don't you do it?
♪ Ain't no harm
in having just a bit more fun
♪ Whether you like it or not
♪ Make no place
for dragging down your face
♪ Don't you know it's
the best one that you got?
♪ So why don't you do it?
♪ Yeah, why don't you do it?
♪ Why don't you do it?
♪ Break that bank
♪ You never know,
you might draw blanks
♪ Then again,
it might sort you out
♪ So why don't you do it, do it,
do it, do it, do it, do it?
♪ Do it
♪ Do it ♪
He emerges.
Good afternoon.
Is it afternoon?
Where's Ernesto? He was
supposed to stay with me.
Don't get mad at Ernie.
He spent
the better part of a day
watching you do your
impression of a baked potato.
I told him to go home,
get some shut-eye.
You hungry?
You want something
besides crackers?
No, I'm fine.
I'll fix myself something.
After my stomach settles.
You're really doing
a number on yourself,
spending so much time
out of the house.
You just had to do it?
Couldn't stand to let
Kim have Mesa Verde.
You had to swipe it from her.
I didn't swipe anything.
We retained our client.
You and Howard never even
heard about Mesa Verde
till Kim brought it to you
on a red velvet pillow.
I need a shower. And I've
got a ton of work to do.
So, if you're
looking for a fight,
Jimmy,
I just don't have it in me.
Jimmy.
Thanks for staying with me.
I know we have our issues.
But if things were reversed,
I hope you know that
I would do the same for you.
You're doing a great job.
You done this before?
No. Not like this.
But we learned about
fractions in school.
You did? What fractions?
Half inch, quarter inch,
eighth inch, sixteenth inch.
Wow.
You know, I got to tell you.
You are much smarter than I
was when I was your age.
Maybe you needed
better teachers.
That could be.
Can I do the drill now?
You promised.
I did, didn't I?
Okay. Get up here.
Now, you're gonna
have to wear these
if you're gonna handle
the heavy machinery.
Why don't you
have to wear them?
Because Pop-Pop's a grown-up.
And grown-ups get to be stupid.
Now, put them on.
All right.
Now, I'm gonna hold this
because it's heavy.
But you pull the trigger
when I say so. Okay?
Now, get your hand on it.
All right, you got it?
Ready.
All right. Ready, set,
pull.
Good job.
Can we do more? -
You line 'em up for me.
Hello?
We're back here!
Wow! What's all this?
We're making
a special hose!
Yeah, that's
a special hose, all right.
I made marks
every three-quarter inch.
Then Pop-Pop put
a piece of wood down,
so he doesn't ruin his table.
Then we line up a drill
and put the hole in the "X".
Wow!
I needed a soaker for the
rhododendrons out back.
Well, Pop-Pop is gonna have to
finish this project on his own,
because we have to go!
But we're not done yet.
No, I'll finish up.
But you, young lady,
were a big help.
Give me a hug.
Ooh. Love you, girl.
Love you.
Thanks, Mike.
You still good for Friday?
Absolutely.
I'll think of
another project by then.
Fantastic.
Bye. Bye.
I have a lunch date already.
Well, break it.
I cannot break it.
Certainly you can, come on.
Will you take
your hands off me?
What are you playing,
osteopath?
All right, temper...
Listen, Walt. You are no longer
my husband and
no longer my boss!
And you're not
going to be my boss.
Well,
it would have worked out
if you'd been satisfied with
just being editor and reporter.
But not you! You had to
marry me, spoil everything!
I wasn't satisfied.
I suppose I proposed to you!
Well,
you practically did.
Making goo-goo eyes at me for
two years until I broke down.
"Walter!"
And I still claim I was tight
the night I proposed to you.
If you'd been
a gentleman you'd have
forgotten all about it.
But not you!
Why, you...
You're losing your eye.
You used to be able
to pitch better than that.
Hello. Yeah. What?
Sweeney?
Well, what can I do for you?