Texas, a place American Idol has come to no end love.
We visited the lone star state six times over the years.
And we've never been disappointed.
# rest of my life #
What was that?
Well, maybe a little.
Get ready to do it all...
Over...
I wouldn't have chosen that song.
I wouldn't have chosen any song.
Again.
This is Dallas.
And this is American Idol.
This week, American Idol sets
up in Dallas, Texas.
The Texans do it big, baby.
It's going down.
It's the second-biggest state in the U.S.,
but its pride is second to none.
Dallas is the best place to be.
I'm never leaving Texas, period.
# god bless Texas #
# with his own hand #
This is the third time we've two-stepped our way into the Big D.
And as a herd of 11,000 hopefuls migrate
to the new cowboys stadium...
Welcome back!
Welcome back to Dallas!
We're loving the Dallas cheer.
# mm, god bless Texas #
And no one is happier to be back than me.
This is my favorite day ever at work.
Who's the guest judge today?
Richard Simmons.
Richard Simmons should come.
Clint Eastwood would be perfect.
Number one on my list.
He'll talk like this.
Yeah. I hate you.
Sadly, Richard and Clint weren't available, so...
So here we are with Neil Patrick Harris.
All right. Thanks.
All joking aside, this guy is no show biz newcomer.
He's been in this business since he was 11, 12 years old.
He's a song-and-dance man.
# put down the remote #
A star of stage and screen.
And we know Neil will have a lot of
encouraging advice for our contestants.
My goal today, Kara, is to shatter the dreams of thousands.
If I can make two, three dozen people cry,
I feel like I've done my job.
While crushing some big Texas dreams,
hopefully Neil and the rest of our judges will also strike gold,
just like we did when we first visited Dallas in Season One.
Kelly Clarkson.
But she's not all we found that year in Dallas.
# gitchie-gitchie-ya-da #
# da-da #
# hey #
# gitchie-gitchie-ya-ya #
# yoo-oo #
'Kay.
Eight seasons later, she's ready to get some more exposure.
My name is Julie Kevelighan.
I am a college student.
But I could be the next American Idol.
I don't believe in giving up.
I'm that... You know, I got that personality.
I'm a leo, you know.
You remember me?
Yes, you did lady Marmalade.
Yup.
And they weren't so thrilled with you.
Are you taking singing lessons?
There was this lady up in Montana.
Get a lawyer and sue her.
No.
I'm gonna still try, you know.
The way I prepared for today...
Oh, sorry.
Taking choir and acting classes.
Well, hopefully this is your year.
And hopefully they have a smile on their face
when they hear you do your song.
Okay.
Good to see you.
Good to see you again, Ryan.
Thank you. Buh-bye.
- Oh, my. - Wow.
Hi.
- Hi. - Hello.
Welcome.
Sparkle.
What's your sign say?
"This is my year"
You wrote the sign?
Yes.
Okay, good, what are you gonna sing?
I'm gonna do "Black velvet".
Great.
By Alannah Myles.
I'm gonna set this sign down.
I think that's probably a good idea.
Okay.
Just...
# up in #
# music's like a heat wave #
# white lightning bound #
# to drive you wild #
# mama's baby's in the heart #
# of every school girl #
# love me tender #
# leaves 'em crying #
# in the aisles #
Ooh.
Okay. All right.
Um, Neil, what did you think of Julie, man?
Well, my first problem was the bottom line of your sign.
The letters just get real small at the end.
It seemed like you might have wanted to start over.
But vocally...
Oh, no.
Yeah, it wasn't a strong...
That was not good.
- Not good. - Can I do another song?
- I don't think so. - No, no, no, just one.
Simon?
Yes, I think you missed off the word "not."
Oh god.
Um, Julie, I mean, I'm being honest.
The whole thing, from the outfit, the makeup, the singing,
everything was wrong.
Okay, Randy, yes or no?
# somewhere #
God.
No.
# over the rainbow #
Julie, you're making it worse.
No.
# bluebirds fly #
Julie...
You changed keys in the middle there, sweet pea.
It's also getting weird.
The voice is not good enough.
Randy, yes or no?
No, no.
Neil?
No, no, no, no, no.
Kara?
I'm sorry, honey.
Sorry, sweetheart.
Thank you.
# let's give them something #
# to talk about #
You've done that, baby.
You've done that.
Charles, help Julie out with her sign.
No, honey.
# love #
Keep singing in the elevator.
Do you think that's gonna help?
That was weird.
You know what I mean?
That's just annoying.
Hey, Julie, how'd it go?
No.
No?
- No. - Why not this time?
I felt if I just would have paid attention to my breathing...
Breath control.
You know...
You know, maybe I can just do a song real quick right now...
No, no, their decision is final.
It's not gonna help.
I just feel like I blew it, that's all.
Breath control.
Yeah.
Okay, well, c'est la vie, right?
Good luck to you. Thank you.
So far, Kelly Clarkson remains Season One's greatest find.
# black velvet #
I should have took a deep breath, what I should have done...
before I sung.
Which I think I did, but...
# black velvet #
# with that little boy's smile #
And the judges gave Julie a lot to think about.
And while she ponders her breathing techniques,
We're gonna head to a break.
In this hour, the search continues for some Texas-sized talent.
- Yes. - Billion percent yes.
My favorite audition of the day.
Have we found the next American Idol?
Look no further, baby,
Because I am the next America's Idol.
Plus, Simon messes with Texas.
It was absolutely atrocious.
As our guest judge messes with Simon.
Don't I get to say something?
Jeez Louise, you invite a guest judge on and...
Do we have a mutiny on the panel here?
This and more...
Get out of here, Simon. You better leave right now.
After the break.
Back with you in the Big D.
It's 11:00 a.m. in Texas,
and even though we didn't start out strong
in the past hour, Dallas has delivered for the ladies.
And if it's Texas-sized talent that we want,
our next guy already has a leg up.
I like to think I can robot just a li... Oh, pick it back up.
My name is Lloyd " big succsexy " Thomas.
Succsexy.
I'm from Dallas, Texas.
I'm 29 years old.
What do you do for a living?
Uh, actually, I'm a dock worker right now for an airline.
It's picking up boxes, pushing boxes.
The worst part about my job that I have...
Did you wash your hands?
is probably my job that I have.
These are my two lovely daughters.
Wait a minute, let me put my wallet away.
These are my lovely daughters right there.
If you can just zoom up.
Oh, if you could just...
We gonna edit that part, right?
I'm born and raised in Dallas, and, you know,
Just a homegrown homeboy, growing up in the projects with,
You know, drugs everywhere, guns everywhere.
And now I've got a family of my own.
This day is so important because I don't want them
to have to ever know what it was like to experience
some of the things that I experienced.
I don't want them to know that
when daddy says, " yeah, you can do anything, baby, "
they'll know we can do anything.
'Cause daddy did it.
Yeah.
There it is. There it is.
And what are you gonna sing?
I'm gonna sing " Overjoyed " by Stevie Wonder.
Good.
# over dreams #
# I've envisioned the perfect #
# come true #
# though you never knew it #
# was of you #
# I've been dreaming #
# and though you don't believe #
# that they do #
# dreams do come true #
Thank you.
That's what's up.
You know, what I love about this show, Lloyd, is that here you are,
you're a dock worker, and you have that voice.
I mean, come on, this guy's working the docks with that voice.
This guy's working the...
That's what I'm saying.
And I love that the show...
I love that the show lets you come here and do that.
I think you have a wonderful voice, but I need to see you really be
as flashy as you are right now as a person.
We can do that.
I like your vibe too.
You got all your positivity jumping off.
That's what it's all about.
Uh, for me, it was my favorite audition of the day.
Get out of here, Simon.
You better leave right now.
He'd love to.
No. Have him stay.
We've got more people...
No, I mean it.
I really, really like you.
I think you're a great singer.
Well done.
Randy, yes or no?
Uh, billion percent yes to Lloyd.
A billion?
Neil?
I give you a yes.
Yeah.
Kara?
100% yes.
Lloyd, you've got four yeses.
Well done.
Welcome to Hollywood, Lloyd.
Thank you. Love you.
Love you.
Keep it real.
Take care.
Yeah!
Oh, my god!
Oh, my goodness, Lord Jesus.
Oh, my Lord Jesus., goodness.
It's tangible.
I wish you could taste what I taste right now.
It's touchable.
It's the taste...
It's readable, and it's reachable.
of victory.
That's what this is.
Delicious.
The only guy to grab the golden ticket so far,
Lloyd Thomas is shining like the lone star of Texas.
And as morning turns to high noon,
it looks like there's gonna be a showdown.
I thought you were just great.
Got absolutely nothing out of that audition, I'm afraid.
I say yes.
Definitely not.
I found it really boring.
A bit rude.
I'm gonna say no.
I'm gonna give you another shot.
Oh, my god.
Simon, yes or no?
I'm gonna say no.
I'm gonna say yes.
I like it.
I love you, Neil Patrick Harris, oh, my god.
I'm scared to disagree with you.
Randy, yes or no?
Nah.
Well, don't I get to say something?
Jeez louise, you invite a guest judge on and bully him around.
Whoa.
Well, it looks like we have a standoff.
Can our next contestant Kimberly Carver keep out of the crossfire?
Hello.
Hi.
Hi, guys.
What a pleasure to be in front of you.
I've dreamed about this forever.
Cool. What are you singing for us today?
Um, I'm actually gonna sing an original if that's okay with you guys.
Wow.
Okay.
# your eyes give you away #
# I know #
# you wanna be my friend #
# I can tell #
# you've been around #
# well, I've heard #
# you've been flirting #
# with the town #
# my poor mother said #
# if you can #
# remember every good woman #
# needs to find herself #
# a real good man #
Thank you.
Wow.
Excellent. Brilliant voice.
Doesn't matter the song original, whatever, whatever.
You can blow, man.
That was really, really good.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Really excellent.
I don't see anything current, anything interesting,
Anything which would make me interested in you as a performer.
So that's why I have an issue.
I disagree with you, Simon.
I thought it was really quite great.
I disagree with Simon too.
Do we have a mutiny on the panel here?
Yeah.
I was just saying, under normal circumstances,
you wouldn't be interested.
No, I would be.
I would be too because the voice would draw me in,
and this is a singing competition.
If it was Jazz TV, yes.
No, because there's a lot of jazz in today's music.
You have a great vibe.
Let's take a vote.
Randy, what do you think?
I say a million percent yes.
You got great vocals.
This is a singing show.
Thank you.
Kara?
Thank you so much.
I'm gonna say yes.
Simon?
I'm gonna say no.
Well, I am gonna say a big yes.
I think you have a great vibe.
Congratulations.
Welcome to Hollywood.
Prove that man on the end that he should be watching you all the time.
I'm gonna impress you next time, you watch.
Welcome to Jazz TV.
# Bum bum bum bum #
Jazz TV... You're so bad.
Simon hated me.
But they totally overrode him, and thank god for Neil Patrick Harris.
I'm gonna have to go back and watch Doogie Howser again.
Thanks to Dr. Howser,
Kimberly leaves with a prescription for Hollywood.
I'm going to Hollywood, baby!
You better follow me there.
Yeah!
Coming up, can the guys play nice?
It's an absolute unanimous no.
What?
Come on.
Or will they have to be whipped into submission?
Who do you want to whip first?
Well, it depends on how this goes.
Oh.
Stay with us as things get wild...
and Texas strikes gold.
I think you're one of the best I've seen for season nine.
Yay!
Welcome back to Dallas.
One thing's for sure, whenever American Idol comes to town,
it's always a big deal.
Thousands of people from all over the country come to us
to help make their dreams come true.
And the media is always on hand to help spread the news.
Big crowds out at Cowboy Stadium in Arlington.
A lot of excitement, a lot of anticipation.
Now let's talk to a couple of folks
that are here to audition this morning.
They are just as eager to find the next American Idol as we are.
And earlier this morning,
they may have done just that.
The show is over because I am the next America's Idol.
My name is Dexter Warren and, you know,
you guys are looking for your next idol.
Well, look no further, baby.
I'm here.
I'm just being honest.
The show is over.
I am very, very, very, very,
very, very, very, very, very,
very sure, when I come through that door,
I will have a golden ticket.
So without further ado, let the games begin.
All right.
- Oh, yeah. - Work it.
Work it.
How are you?
Fine. And you?
I'm good.
What's your name?
Dexter Warren.
So what are you gonna sing for us today?
Um, "If I ever fall in love again" by Shai.
Whenever you're ready.
# the very first time #
# that I saw your brown eyes #
# your lips said hello #
# and I said hi #
# I knew right then #
# you were the one #
# but I was caught up #
# caught up #
# in physical attraction #
# but to my satisfaction #
# baby, you're more #
# than just a friend #
# and if I ever fall in love #
# so true #
# I will be sure #
# that the lady's #
# just like you #
Nice.
Oh. Oh, Dexter.
Kara?
Dexter, man, I don't...
I don't... Randy, help.
Help, Randy.
No, dude, look, I mean, really, right?
That looked like it hurt.
Can I say something, please?
It's just the nerves.
It's just the song or whatever.
I have another song that I've been trying to...
Dawg...
I can do it much better.
Dexter, by you saying you've got something else
- to sing is not gonna help you. -Yeah, that was...
That was not the best audition, dude.
Singing's not your thing, though, dawg.
I'm telling you, man.
Trust me, man. Trust.
All right, Kara, yes or no?
I mean, it's just not gonna work, honey.
I'm sorry.
Simon?
It's no. Sorry, Dexter.
Yeah, sorry, man.
Maybe next time.
Nice to meet you.
But thanks for liking the show.
Thank you.
But you've got a good attitude, good smile.
I like you, Dexter.
That smile will take you far in life, I promise you.
It will.
It turns out Dexter's smile barely made it outside the judging room.
And as the day one auditions continued...
That's a no, sweetheart.
Sorry.
I don't think the voice is strong enough.
I'm gonna say no.
Sorry.
Many of the big dreams of the Dallas hopefuls suddenly came to an end.
It's not worth my tears.
I don't know why I'm crying.
Making it difficult to take it all in.
# and I can't breathe #
# without you #
# but I have to #
All right, everybody,
group hug.
# breathe #
# without you #
# but I have to #
Back inside, the judges are also in need of a sigh of relief.
So while they take a break,
I get an update from guest judge Neil Patrick Harris.
What have you thought about this group of contestants so far today?
I've been surprised by the talent.
I thought it would be a lot of nos and a few yeses,
but we've sent a lot... A fair amount of people through.
Do you find it tough to be honest with them, or not?
People get reamed out every single week on this show,
week after week, multiple songs.
You know more than anyone.
So it's like, if they can't handle this heat,
that kitchen is the broiler.
Looking to take full advantage of a refreshed group of judges,
our next contestant plans on leaving a striking impression.
My name is Erica Rhodes.
I'm 23, and I'm from Irving, Texas.
What do you do in Irving?
Well, right now, I'm a grad student, but I also act.
I've been acting since I was little.
The first major thing that I was on was Barney & Friends.
Really?
I started off as a Barney kid.
# Barney is a dinosaur #
This panda has always been special to me.
I was innocent, sweet, child-like.
I do feel the need to show people that I've grown up from Barney.
Is this part of your...
Yes, it is.
Performance?
Don't tell nobody.
All right, I won't say anything about your gloves.
Today for my audition,
I think I'm going to take a different approach.
Wow. With a whip.
Come on in, Barney.
So who do you want to whip first?
Okay, it says here that you used to be a dinosaur or something.
I used to be on barney & friends.
What?
I knew I recognized you.
What is that?
Do a little bit of the Barney song in this outfit, though.
Sing a little bit of it.
Okay.
# I love you #
# you love me #
# we're a happy family #
Oh, my god.
Oh, I'm getting the creeps.
# with a great, big hug #
# and a kiss from me to you #
# won't you say #
# you love me too #
Oh.
Barney would be so proud.
And then I whip all my friends.
And then I spank them 'cause they're naughty.
That's what I do.
Okay, Erica, what are you gonna sing today?
I'm going to sing " Free your mind " by En vogue.
Great.
Okay.
# I wear tight clothing #
# high-heeled shoes #
# but that don't mean #
# that I'm a prostitute #
# no, no #
# I might date another #
# race or color #
# it doesn't mean I don't like #
# my strong black brother #
# ooh la la la la #
# la la la la #
# free your mind #
# and the rest will follow #
Ok. We got it.
We got it. Thank you, Erica.
Okay, well, look, you definitely made an impression here, Erica.
That was cool.
Um, what's the big dream here?
The big dream is...
I know what mine is.
Yeah, exactly, exactly.
I want people to know that Barney kids grow up.
To be dirty little girls.
Well, I'm not dirty.
I mean, my role model is Janet Jackson.
What do you expect?
I do like people who make an effort.
You've gone from the kids thing to this.
It takes guts.
It's really rare that someone comes in here
and they're like, you know,
"I'm just gonna do my thing,
This is who I am,
and here it comes," you know.
And I really like that about you.
- Great presence. - Okay, Randy, yes or no?
I like her. I'm gonna say yes.
- Neil? - I think you might actually do really well.
I say yes.
- Kara? - Definitely.
Erica, you're through.
Welcome to Hollywood. You made it.
Thank you so much.
Trip down memory lane and four yeses later...
Contestants are still crying in Dallas.
Who cries as a dominatrix?
Barney dominatrixes.
But at least these are tears of joy.
I think we're gonna let them catch their breath.
We'll come back with more auditions right here on American Idol.
Yes! Ha ha ha ha!
You think I'm crazy, don't ya?
No.
Yeah! We made it!
Yeah! Whoo-hoo!
And, remember, I love you.
When we come back, will the gold rush continue?
It was terrible.
Are you sending me to Hollywood?
- Oh, God. - Plus, they've beaten the odds...
The first thing that went through my mind was
that I was gonna lose her.
Call it a miracle.
You know, I don't know what it is.
But will they need a miracle
to make it to Hollywood?
Voice-wise, I'm not jumping out of my chair.
Welcome back to American Idol.
We started the day with 11,000 strong.
And now the Day One auditions
are starting to wind down.
Throughout the day, several contestants
have played the odds and cashed in big.
I'm not letting this go.
Now the final contestant of the day
will try to do the same.
Only, life has dealt him a hand in which
the odds are stacked against him.
My name's Dave Pittman,
and I'm 27 years old,
and I'm from Gassville, Arkansas.
I was first diagnosed with
Tourette's Syndrome when...
when I was... I was nine years old.
Tourette's syndrome is a neurological disorder,
and it affects the nervous system.
The symptoms that go along with Tourette's is,
You know, maybe blinking of the eyes, you know,
shaking the head sometimes, clearing of the throat.
Sometimes, you know,
when Tourette's has been bothering me or something,
You know, Dad and I, we'll go out and, you know,
we'll spend some time together in the woods fishing.
The crazy thing is that it doesn't...
It doesn't affect me at all when I'm singing.
Call it a miracle.
I don't know what it is.
I used to see Tourette's as a curse,
you know, but I consider it a blessing.
It's taught me a lot about myself.
It's made me who I am.
- So you are Dave Pittman? - Yes, I am.
It says that you're 27,
- from mountain home, Arkansas. - Yes.
So you think you're the next American Idol, dog?
Oh, yeah. I'm ready for this.
This has been my dream since I've been a kid.
What you gonna sing?
I'm gonna sing " Bring it on home to me " by Sam Cooke.
Do it.
# if you ever #
# change your mind #
# about leaving #
# leaving me behind #
# oh #
# bring it to me #
# bring your sweet loving #
# bring it on home #
# to me, yeah #
# Oh, yeah #
# you know, i've tried #
# to treat you right #
- Thank you, David. - What do you think, Neil?
- What do you think, Man? - I really liked your voice.
- I appreciate that. - Weird elephant in the room.
Do you have... Do you have, like,
Tourette's syndrome or something?
Yes, I do. I have Tourette's Syndrome.
But you don't...
That doesn't happen when you're singing.
How crazy is that?
- That's wild. - I didn't see it.
But your voice is just great.
I mean, you have a really cool look and...
Appreciate that.
Yeah, I liked your voice too, Man.
I thought you were a really good singer.
It's a tough song to sing.
You did it very nicely. Let's take a vote.
Simon, yes or no?
I think people are gonna like you.
Yeah, and I thought you were terrific.
Kara?
I want to give you another shot.
- Yes. - Neil?
I think you're crazy brave.
And good for you.
Really good voice. I say yes.
Dude, I'm gonna say yes too.
Welcome to Hollywood. Yeah!
Thank you, guys, so much.
Yeah!
This is, like, just one step closer to my dream.
I can't even hardly talk.
It's amazing. Whoo!
You're going to Hollywood!
As day one comes to a close,
Dave lassoed
the last golden tickets in Dallas.
Hollywood, baby.
Hollywood.
Proving dreams still do come true.
And he, along with 14 others that made it to Hollywood,
couldn't think of a better way to celebrate...
- I'm gonna say yes. - Super-big yes for me.
I'll give you another shot.
You got four yeses, darling.
Than to have a party.
Welcome to Hollywood.
# here I am #
# for the first time #
# look to my right #
- Yes. - Thank you.
# this is all so crazy #
# I'm nodding my head #
# like yeah #
It's a yes.
# moving my hips like yeah #
# it's a party in the USA #
I'm gonna whip it in Hollywood.
It's the golden ticket!
Ticket!
Coming up...
Tomorrow, a Jonas brother.
Girls screaming everywhere.
Day two, can we wrangle up any more talent?
That was excellent.
- My favorite of the day. - After this.
Welcome to the second day of
the roundup here in Dallas.
Welcome back to the Big D.
Whoo!
The crowd is all saddled up and ready to go.
All we need now are the judges.
Hi. Big D in the house.
And our guest judge for today
is none other than Joe Jonas.
I hear there was a little confusion
about who Joe Jonas is.
He's 1/3 of the world's busiest brothers.
And wherever he goes,
one word describes him...
Heartthrob.
This is actually our hometown.
So to see future stars hopefully coming out
of Dallas is always exciting for us.
All right, let's do this.
But Joe isn't just another pretty face.
In the past year,
he and his brothers have become so big,
even Randy Jackson wants in on the act.
I'm now a member of the Jonas brothers.
You're a member of the Jonas brothers?
Unofficially, but,
officially, yeah.
So the contestants are set.
The cameras are rolling.
And there's a slight chill in the room.
Yeah, man, I'm saying, dude.
It's cold in here.
First up is Todrick Hall,
and he has the job of being the warm-up act.
- Welcome to Dallas, you all. - Thank you.
You were with fantasia in the color purple?
Yes, I was.
And now it's time to step into
the spotlight and be the idol?
I'm gonna try, I'm gonna try.
All right, well, let's hear it.
This is a special song
that I wrote just for y'all.
# Todrick is my name #
# and I'm here to play #
# a part in your game #
# hopped a plane #
# took a train just to claim #
# my 15 minutes of fame #
# and to see Kara decked #
# and dressed #
# Simon's face looking #
# so unimpressed #
# sitting there like a bump #
# on a log #
# Randy, what I got to do #
# to be your dawg #
# tell me, do I have #
# to dress up like I'm from #
# a crazy house #
# or sing like William hung #
# for you to see #
# there's some potential #
# in little, ol' me #
# and tell me, do I have #
# to get down on my knees #
# in my $300 jeans #
# cause I would #
# if it meant to me #
# that maybe you could #
# just send me to Hollywood #
- Thank you. - Whoo! I liked that.
That was awesome.
- That was cute. - That was cool, man.
Very good.
Simon, I can't get a clap or nothing?
That's good.
Thank you.
I'll take one.
Dude, I think you one of the best
I've seen in this audition
for season nine, because, dude,
that was excellent.
- Thank you. - It was awesome, man.
Definitely you have star power, for sure.
Thank you very much.
My feeling is, I think you're a nice guy,
I think you're a good singer,
I think it was a cutesy audition.
Voice-wise, I'm not jumping out of my chair.
I'm jumping out of my chair.
Okay, we're gonna see how high Randy's gonna jump.
- Yes or no? - Yes.
Thank you.
- Joe? - Yeah.
- Kara? - Yes.
Four yeses.
Welcome to Hollywood, Todrick.
I'm going to Hollywood!
I thought he was good.
I made it.
We're gonna take this ticket,
and we're gonna go all the way to the top.
Day two is off to a great start.
And Todrick is head over heels with excitement.
But he wasn't the only one.
# I'm sitting here #
# so lonely #
# so lonesome I could cry #
I'm gonna say yes. I'll give you another shot.
- Joe? - Yeah.
Definitely.
You've got four yeses, sweetheart.
- Yay. Thank you. - Yeah.
- Yes. - Thank you so much.
I'm gonna say yes.
Michael, I'm gonna say yes as well.
- Whoo! - You're through to Hollywood.
Whoo!
# I'll meet you halfway #
# my love #
# won't you do the same #
I'm gonna say yes.
# Hollywood #
- I say yeah. - I'm gonna say yes.
It's a yes for me.
Welcome to Hollywood.
Looking to continue Day two's gold rush...
is Megan Wright.
And she's happy not to
face today's audition alone.
My name is Megan Wright.
I'm 20, and I'm from Richardson, Texas.
My parents are divorced.
They got divorced five years ago.
They're both remarried,
And I have my little brother.
It's just me and him.
I'm really glad I have her,
cause, without her,
it would just be boring.
If I make it to Hollywood,
I can't express what it will mean to my brother.
He will be so excited.
I may give her a big,
old hug and never stop.
Party all night! Uh-huh.
I really want her to be the next American Idol.
- You do? - Yes.
- What do you think America will think? - Yes.
- Hello. - Hi, hi, hi.
- Hi, hi, hi. - I'm excited. Hi.
What are you gonna sing?
"To Make You Feel My Love."
"To Make You Feel My Love"
Okay. Go for it.
# when the rain is blowing #
# in your face #
# and the whole world #
# is on your case #
# I could offer you #
# a warm embrace #
# to make you feel my love #
# I'd go hungry #
# I'd go blind for you #
# I'd go crawling #
# down the avenue #
Thank you very much, Megan.
- Thank you, Simon. - Wow.
- I really like you. - Interesting.
Thank you.
I mean, you really confused me.
from walking in with that outfit,
I really thought this was gonna be a joke.
Oh, man.
And then you open your mouth like that,
and you have a great voice.
- Thank you. - I mean, a really beautiful voice.
- Very moving. - Thank you.
Funny enough, I disagree with Kara
about what you're wearing.
Gee, imagine.
Because I think that, in a way,
you're not trying too hard like
we see with a lot of other people,
and I like the surprise element from you.
Thank you.
And if that's what makes you comfortable, then fine.
- Randy, yes or no? - I love this girl. Yes!
Thank you.
- Joe? - Yeah.
- Kara? - My favorite of the day. Yes.
Uh, so it's a no from Kara.
It's a yes from me.
- Ah, yes. - Thank you, guys.
Yes.
We're 2,000% positive.
Oh, I'm just one step closer
to being the next American Idol.
Megan's Idol dream is still alive.
And Dawson gets to cheer on his big sister
all the way to Hollywood.
Coming up...
She's a survivor.
The first thing that went through my mind
was that I was gonna lose her.
But can she make it through her audition?
Plus, everyone wonders why Simon's mood always sour?
If anyone ever asks me in my life
what my nightmares look and sound like,
I'm gonna refer to that.
I have my theory.
And I'll share it after the break.
Dallas, Texas has been our home
for the past couple of days.
And aside from being left on top of a very tall building,
I've had a pretty good time.
Hello, Dallas.
Since I've been here,
I even managed to find a new job.
Mm.
But I'm still keeping my old one.
This is my favorite day ever at work.
I'm not gonna see any contestants.
I'm hanging today right here.
But upstairs, I was missing out on a party.
My name's Vanessa Johnston.
I'm 22 years old.
I am the next American Idol.
Yeah!
Whoo!
I am super optimistic.
I just look at the positive things in everything.
Come on!
Hopefully that can go through the TV,
and people will be like,
"Wow, I need to be happy all the time like her."
# sign and dance #
Oh! Oh, my gosh.
Hi, how are y'all?
Welcome.
Dallas, yes, whoo!
Yay. Dallas!
What's your favorite color?
Pink!
I didn't get that.
I really love teal too.
Okay, so what song?
I'm singing "At Last" by Etta James.
- Great song. - Okay.
# at last #
# my love #
# has come along #
# my lonely days #
# are over #
# and life is like a song #
# at last #
# my love has come along #
# my lonely days are over #
# life is like a song #
- Oh. - Sorry.
Vanessa, Honey,
You're doing this Britney thing with your head.
I like it cause you kept moving
like the notes were over there.
- Yeah. - Over here.
Maybe it's back there. I don't know.
Vanessa, if anyone ever asks me in my life
what my nightmares look and sound like,
I'm gonna refer to that.
I'm sorry.
That's what keeps me up at night.
All right, you know what,
we should just vote on you,
Vanessa, cause I think we know
where this is going.
- Should I sing another one? - What?
No, Sweetie.
One is definitely...
Never.
Okay, Randy, yes or no?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- It's okay. - Here's the positive.
I'm definitely gonna remember you, but no.
That's good. I'm excited.
Great, here's some even better news.
- It's four nos. - Yay.
Nice to meet you.
Nice... it's so nice to meet y'all, for real.
You're funny.
Wow.
So it's a no.
Simon said I was his worst nightmare.
Why are you clapping?
Vanessa might not be going to Hollywood...
It's okay if you say I'm your worst nightmare,
but at least you're dreaming about me, huh?
A-ha!
But she still finds a way to see the upside.
That's the strangest thing
that's ever happened to me.
- Really? - Let's do it again.
But thanks to Simon, what goes up...
# I want to hold her tight #
Must come down.
Cody.
I think the problem is you.
Okay, hold on, let's stop the tape.
We're in our ninth season, and,
year after year, fans talk about
how mean Simon can be.
That was terrible.
- You're horrible. - So are you.
It was painful.
I've heard some brilliant singers in my time.
You are not one of them.
But as my friend,
I feel I need to take this moment
to defend him to you.
Okay, start the tape.
You see, in a single audition tour,
we will visit seven cities,
each with a stadium full of Idol hopefuls.
We listen to thousands of voices...
I'm sorry. I go so flat there.
Hear many stories...
Got a pretty nasty blood blister once.
And watch America try to dance, beg...
- I am ready. - No, you're not.
Yes, I am.
And talk their way to Hollywood.
I hate watching movies with fish cause they're always like,
"what just happened?"
While we at American Idol spare you from
having to listen to this...
and see this...
Not part of our performance.
Simon has the job of sitting through it all.
It's hard being Simon Cowell.
But he does it all for you,
America, because,
every once in a while,
we find someone special.
And hoping she fits
that bill is the last contestant of the Dallas auditions,
16-year-old Christian Spears.
I was diagnosed with leukemia on my 4th birthday.
Being so young, you know,
you don't really know what's going on
and why your hair's falling out
and why you're going into surgery.
When they first told me
that Christian was diagnosed with cancer,
the first thing that went through my mind
was that I was gonna lose her.
# I promise you #
For them to say, you know,
one more day and she wouldn't be here,
It's just hard.
# when your heart is filled #
# with sorrow #
And when I was eight,
a blessing came through for me
because I was in remission.
So I'm an eight-year cancer survivor now.
I always told her, you know,
no matter what you want to do,
I'll work for the rest of my life,
I want you to be happy.
So I tell her all the time,
it's written for her,
so she's supposed to be here.
# you'll find my footprints #
- Hi. - Hello.
- How you guys doing? - Good.
- How are you? - I'm great.
So what are you gonna sing?
I'm gonna be singing "All I Could do Is Cry" by Etta James.
Great.
# I heard #
# church bells were ringing #
# a choir singing #
# I saw my love #
# walk down the aisle #
# on her finger #
# I heard them promise #
# till death do us part #
# each word #
# was a pain #
# in my heart #
Thank you, sweetheart. Randy?
Dude, I think you're really good.
At 16, I'm so, so impressed.
- I love it. - Thank you.
- Joe? - You're definitely very confident.
And a beautiful voice.
You got a big, natural gift.
And I think, when you were singing,
I didn't sense any fear from you,
and, you know, that is really rare in a 16-year-old.
I think you're an incredibly brave person.
And I like you a lot.
I like you too.
Randy, yes or no?
A billion percent yes.
- Joe? - Definitely yes.
- Kara? - Absolutely.
Christian, you got a full house.
- Whoo! - Welcome to Hollywood, Christian.
This golden ticket means that I'm really here,
that I made it.
Is there any better feeling?
No. There's not.
I have yet to find one.
This is so amazing.
We're going to Hollywood!
A happy ending here in Dallas.
And Christian is golden ticket number 17
for the Day two auditions.
We're going to Hollywood!
Making it a grand total of 31 winners
for the city of Dallas...
A number that meets the judges' approval.
It's a wrap.
We made the trip back to the Lone Star State
to find the magic we found so many times before.
Well, whether Dallas can repeat its past or not
will be determined in time.
Goodbye, Dallas.
Hello, Hollywood!
So for now it's time to "mooove" on out to the next stop
on the audition tour...
Yee-haw!
As our search for the next American Idol continues.
Make sure y'all come back now, y'hear?
Next Tuesday on Idol...
We reach new heights in the Mile High City
as season nine heads to Denver, Colorado.
Denver rocks! Whoo!
And get ready as the altitude brings out the tension.
Please get that camera out of my face.
The terrible...
You just killed every cat in.
And the unstoppable talent.
# I'm the only one #
Best voice today in Denver.
And one Denver contestant takes it to the limit.
You won't believe your eyes.