Tonight, the event you've been waiting for is finally here.
I am gonna be the new judge on American Idol.
As Ellen Degeneres takes her permanent place at the panel.
You should put some shoes on.
It's filthy here.
Hollywood is a disgusting town.
Together we commence Hollywood week.
We're in Hollywood, baby!
100,000 came to us from every corner of the country.
I'm a bartender.
I'm a police officer.
I'm a receptionist, but I could be...
But I could be...
We could be...
the next American Idol!
and after our exhaustive
seven-city search, we discovered 181 of the nation's best.
Very, very nice.
That was amazing.
You could be the potential winner.
whoo!
But now the most difficult test of all.
I don't care about them.
Man.
They were such idiots.
I hated everything about that.
I did everything I could!
After this process, we'll be down to 12 guys and 12 girls.
This will no doubt be the toughest week of their lives,
because this is Hollywood week.
And this is American Idol.
whoo!
It's 7:00 a.m. in California,
and the sun has risen on Day one of Hollywood week.
From around the country, 181 hopefuls have arrived...
Hollywood!
taking the first step towards the chance of a lifetime.
Oh, my god!
There's hundreds of people here, and I have to stand out.
Living the dream, baby.
I'm just ready to do what I got to do, and do my best.
whoo!
I can't even imagine how much it would change my life,
but I am so ready.
Here we go.
Adding to the pressure,
performing on the most high-profile stage in the world,
the Kodak Theatre.
As the hopefuls take their seats,
anxiously waiting for their shot...
I feel so nervous.
I'm, like, shaking.
they're not the only ones about to start a new journey.
Please say hi to your new judge on American Idol,
Ellen Degeneres.
I... I don't know how you feel right now,
but I'll tell you one thing.
When people say, you know, "what do you know about music?"
I'll tell you what I do know.
I do know what it's like to stand on stage
and try to please an entire room full of people.
That is a hard thing to do.
There's been a lot said about what kind of a judge
you will be on this show.
Uh, kind, generous, honest, but at the same time pretty direct,
and one of the few people, I think, that can be honest
with Simon about how he takes on the contestants.
Yes.
Is that your plan?
I'm sorry.
I wasn't listening.
Goodbye.
I think she's gonna fit in just fine.
So our new team is assembled and
ready to start Hollywood week season nine.
so this is it, huh?
When I come on, you leave.
Let the games begin.
Knew you were gonna say that.
But for the contestants, this is no laughing matter.
Here's how this round will work.
Like in years past, the contestants will
come out on the stage in groups of eight.
They'll have a choice.
They can sing either a cappella,
or with an instrument.
And this round is sudden death.
That means you're either moving on...
You're through to the next round.
or heading straight home.
You didn't make it.
Are you ready, judges?
Yeah, yeah.
Stand by, stand by.
Let's go, guys.
Hollywood week starts right now.
In the first line, two familiar faces from
the road. Skiiboski from Atlanta, and Katie Stevens from Boston.
She shared her family's emotional struggle at her first audition.
I'm really close with my grandmother.
she has Alzheimer's.
She's probably not gonna remember me for much longer,
so I want her to see me succeed in my dream
before she forgets who I am.
But how will this 17-year-old deal
with the bright lights of Hollywood?
# for once in my life #
# I have someone who needs me #
# someone I've needed so long #
# for once unafraid #
# I can go where love leads me #
# somehow I know #
# I'll be strong #
# for once I can touch #
# what my heart #
# used to dream of #
# long before I knew #
# oh someone warm like you #
# would make #
# my dreams come true #
# yeah #
# for... #
Thank you.
Actually, you're quite good.
Yes!
I remember when we saw you the first time, and I said then,
"great natural talent".
Thank you.
Next up, who could forget...
Skiiboski, baby.
You already know.
That's right, but will he
bring his swagger to Hollywood?
How you doing?
I'm all right.
What's your name?
Skiiboski.
Oh, yeah.
# I know #
# you want to leave me #
# but I refuse to let you go #
# if I have to beg, plead #
# for your sympathy #
# I don't mind #
# 'cause you mean #
# that much to me #
# ain't too proud to beg #
# sweet darling #
# please don't leave me girl #
All right, Skiibo... ski?
You frighten me.
You were... you were stalking us.
You were like a leopard behind the cage.
Looking... I was watching you.
Look at us like...
I'm gonna get you.
Looked like you were gonna get us.
- Standing in front of y'all, - I know. I know.
this is the American dream.
Of course, but seriously,
um, don't frighten your audience.
Don't... don't get so intense, you know?
Sexy and scary, it's a fine line.
Okay.
All right?
So...
anyway, thanks so much.
Thank you, Skiiboski.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Now the contestants have had a chance to sing in a group of eight.
The judges will compare notes and deliberate.
We had yes, yes, no, no.
They will then divide the group into two lines,
by asking certain people to step forward or back.
But only one of the lines will be going through.
The judges wrapping up their deliberation.
Now it's time for the verdict.
So who's in? Who's out?
Let's go.
Marcus and Christy, step forward,
and, Antonio, step forward.
I'm sorry, guys.
You didn't make it, but thank you very much.
So Katie's in, but Skiiboski's out.
And while the winners celebrate...
Whoo!
looks like someone's not going down without a fight.
I just got to know,
what... what was it?
You're just not a very good singer.
You failed the audition.
It's time to go.
And my name is...
# Skiiboski #
# yeah #
I would change your name, to start.
Yeah.
So this season's Hollywood week is in full swing,
but we're only getting started.
Coming up, they blew the judges away at their first audition.
You got mad vocals, dude.
That was excellent.
When you are good, you're really good.
None of my friends is gonna believe this.
Whoo!
But what happens when they face the music at the Kodak?
Unbelievable.
Plus, some of the most amazing performances in Hollywood week history.
Genius.
It's 11:30 a.m. on day one of Hollywood week.
181 of the country's best singers have been invited to the
prestigious Kodak theatre for their one shot on center stage.
And for those waiting in the wings, the tension is mounting.
It's a big day.
And it's not helping that for the past hour,
Simon's been on the warpath.
I hated everything about that.
That was painful.
Wrong, wrong, wrong.
Oh, my god.
Think the front row or back row made it?
It's a good thing our new judge Ellen knows how to sugar coat.
I'm tired as it is,
that almost put me right out.
It was crazy, I think.
um, in a bad way, crazy.
I'm sorry.
Where are you from?
Florida.
Okay.
You should put some shoes on here.
It's filthy here.
This is... Hollywood is a disgusting town.
Seems the comic relief is lightening the mood in the theater,
but for those about to take the stage,
it's not helping at all, including country girl Vanessa Wolfe.
Try and keep it cool.
And Andrew Garcia, the father who's here to
make a better life for his struggling family.
I love you.
I love you too, you know?
Today, he's about to take a huge risk.
I am singing Paula Abdul's "Straight up".
I've done my own little rendition, hopefully they like it.
# lost in a dream #
# don't know which #
# way to go #
# mm #
# if you are all that you seem #
# then baby I'm moving #
# way too slow #
# oh #
# I been a fool before #
# wouldn't like to get my love #
# caught in the slamming door #
# how 'bout some #
# information please #
# oh #
# straight up now tell me #
# do you really want to love #
# me forever #
# oh #
# am I caught in a hit-and-run #
# straight up now tell me #
# is it gonna be #
# you and me forever #
# oh #
# are you just having fun #
Andrew,
that was genius.
Oh, thank you.
Genius.
Paula would be screaming and yelling and clapping and dancing.
Exactly, dude.
She would be doing this for you right now.
Like, dying, and...
Thank you.
You just owned that moment,
and interpreted something in a way...
similar to the way Adam did last season,
when he would take a song and flip it.
Thank you.
Great job.
Thank you so much.
That was ri... ridiculous.
And after hearing Andrew's rave reviews,
Vanessa's nerves are at a breaking point.
After all, she's a long way away from Vonore, Tennessee.
I don't really have a life.
Never goes to the movies or the mall or anything.
I'm stuck.
I can't get out.
But then one day in Atlanta, everything changed.
You stand out in the crowd for me, and I like you.
Welcome to Hollywood, Vanessa!
Ow!
Yeah!
Whoo!
Man, I'm going to Hollywood.
I'm gonna ride on a aeroplane.
What's life without a risk or two?
Ow.
Now she'll take another risk,
leaving everything she knows behind.
first day in the rest of your life, girl.
# ooh #
Bye.
I just can't hardly take this.
Having never left home before, it's all a new experience for Vanessa.
So fancy.
I cannot believe this is happening.
# ooh #
This is a chance to make something of myself.
Just a big, nervous moment.
This is the moment.
Here they come.
Hi.
Hello, my name is Vanessa Jo Wolfe.
In the mic.
Microphone.
Oh, yeah.
Hello.
# all I can say #
# is that my life #
# is pretty plain #
# I like watching the puddles #
# gather rain #
# and all I can do #
# is just pour some tea #
# for two #
# and speak my point of view #
# but it's not sane #
Thank you.
You're unique.
I think you have a unique quality that you should embrace,
and just really just accept who you are.
You're... you're hiding inside and scared to death,
and you got to let go of that, 'cause those nerves are gonna kill ya.
Thanks.
Now it's judgment time for this line.
Oh, no.
I liked her.
Which also includes worship pastor, Tasha Layton.
Yes, yes.
No, yes.
The tension is palpable.
Everyone on pins and needles,
waiting to find out what is in their future.
Debbie, stage manager giving the cue to go.
Andrew, step forward.
With Andrew stepping forward,
Vanessa can only hope her name is called next.
Front row...
Congratulations.
We'll see you tomorrow.
You made it through to the next round.
Back row, end of the line.
Thank you.
Andrew moves on,
but we say good-bye to the country girl who stole our hearts.
My family's gonna be disappointed, but...
you know, I just... I blew it.
I'm sorry, mom.
And as morning turned to afternoon,
plenty more came so far to have their dreams cut short.
You've got a frustrated look on your face.
I think they made a mistake.
Yeah?
# but that's not #
# what gets me #
Sorry, guys.
# what hurts the most #
# was being so close #
Come on, sweetheart.
Let's go.
Let's go back home.
# watching you walk away #
# and never knowing #
This was the ticket to get out of Vonore.
I took a risk, and it... it didn't pay off.
# is what I #
# was trying to do #
When we return, more incredible performances on center stage.
You're really a great singer.
Who will survive the wrath of the judges?
That was painful.
Stay tuned.
You never know what might happen during Hollywood week.
I hated everything about that.
It's 3:30 p.m. on day one of Hollywood week.
And back inside the Kodak Theatre,
things are not so picture perfect for some memorable faces from the early auditions.
Like Cornelius Edwards,
whose pants-splitting performance in Orlando seemed to be his only asset.
# cowgirl, take me away #
Cornelius, why did you choose that song?
And Maegan Wright, whose little brother was a huge support in Dallas.
I really want her to be the next American Idol.
# and I wonder #
# whose loving you #
It was a little all over the place.
Okay.
It's heart-breaking to have to go home.
It really is.
It meant everything to me.
And who could forget Amadeo Diricco,
who charmed America with his big family and even bigger personality?
But in Hollywood, he failed to find his voice.
# 'cause this #
# fine old world #
# it keeps spinning around #
That was not good.
I came here to be the best me I can be.
I ask you for another chance.
I'm begging you.
Please.
Amadeo, you shouldn't be begging,
'cause you're not gonna get a second chance.
Seriously.
I really thought that this was my chance, and I didn't want
to just walk away from it.
I figured let me ask.
Can't hurt to ask.
But Orlando's Janell Wheeler hopes she'll stick around here for a little longer.
I cannot go home.
I want to be here so bad.
I want to be the next American Idol so bad.
# he said #
# hey sister #
# it's really, really nice #
# to meet you #
# I just met this #
# five foot seven #
# guy who's just my type #
# like the way he's speaking #
# his confidence is peaking #
# don't like his baggy jeans #
# but I might like #
# what's underneath them #
# no I've never been to M.I.A. #
# I heard... #
That was amazing.
Amazing.
I loved it.
Yeah, that was a good audition.
Well done.
Thank you so much.
So Janell was an easy yes, and off to the next round.
But as the day continued,
others failed to strike a chord with their instruments.
Maybe learn how to play the guitar.
# people keep talking #
# talking 'bout people #
I hated everything about that performance.
# I seen a rainbow #
# yesterday #
# too many storms come and go #
# leave a trace #
# of not one god-given ray #
# clear unconditional skies #
# dry tears from my eyes #
# no lonely cries #
Thank you.
Can I be honest with you?
That was painful.
# sweet love #
# don't you ever go away #
Bossa will be appearing nightly at the Holiday Inn,
Columbus, on Highway 52.
And after seeing so many people crash and burn with their
instruments, 16-year-old Hayley Vaughn starts to second-guess herself.
Hopefully I can perform well,
and the nerves will leave me somewhere along as
I'm walking up to sing, 'cause I'm pretty nervous, and I'm totally scared.
But she shouldn't be, after the high praise she received in Denver.
Million percent yes.
I love this girl.
Now, armed with her guitar,
can she have the same impact?
# it's a revolution #
# throw your hands up #
# 'cause we never gave in #
# we'll sing Hallelujah #
# Hallelujah #
# oh #
# yeah #
Yo.
I actually kind of like it.
It's very interesting to me.
Kind of a pop-country girl.
16. Interesting.
Thank you.
Also in this line, someone who's on the other end of the age range,
28-year-old rocker mom, Mary Powers.
Hello.
At her L.A. audition, she not only brought her voice...
Rock it, girl.
but also her biggest fan.
Are you sure this isn't my daughter?
# I'm safe up high #
# nothing can touch me #
# and why do I feel #
# this party's over #
# no pain inside #
# you're like perfection #
# and how do I feel this good #
# sober #
You have an amazing voice, and you were very in that song.
Really good.
Thank you.
Now it's the moment of truth for the country girl and the rocker.
I think she's gonna get annoying.
I like her better than her.
All right.
Stephanie, step forward.
Kiera, step forward.
Front row, it's the end of the line.
Sorry, you didn't make it.
Back row, you're through to the next round.
It's an emotional victory for both ladies.
I'm so proud of you.
You did so good.
Thank you.
My whole life, my family's life, everything, is gonna change.
And it's... it's... it's amazing.
Oh!
We'll check back in with them on group day.
And back on stage, the final results of the day.
Maddy, step forward.
Claire, step forward.
I'm sorry.
Claire, step back.
Danny, step forward.
Tori, step forward.
Now, Maddy, step back.
Danny, step to your left a little bit.
Claire, step forward.
And then step back real quick.
You're all going through.
That was funny.
You sadist.
Congratulations, you're through.
# move on up #
And among those moving on up, Todrick Hall from Dallas...
Charity Vance from Chicago.
I know.
I'm, like, shaking.
I'm so excited, I can't believe it.
# so keep on pushing #
And Boston native, Ashley Rodriguez.
I'm staying another day.
Aah!
# move on up #
whoo!
46 contestants have made it through.
At the end of day one in Hollywood...
That's a wrap everybody.
We're out.
Tomorrow we come back and do it all over again.
We start from scratch with new contestants after the break.
Have a good night. Bye.
# we made it #
# ooh, ooh #
After the break, it's day two of Hollywood week,
and that means a whole new crop of the nation's best hit the spotlight.
This could be the most important day of your life.
There's no turning back.
Who survives?
You have conviction.
And who sees their demise?
That was ridiculous.
It's day two of Hollywood week at the world-famous Kodak Theater.
Yesterday, half the contestants took the stage
for their all-important shot in front of the judges.
Safe to say it was a brutal day.
Horrible song choice.
Horrible performance.
Just didn't get it.
It was very karaoke.
It was weird for me.
I don't know.
It was really, really... dull.
- Did you like it? - Uh, I loved it.
But today is a fresh start for a new batch of contestants.
As the judges settle in, Simon has some inspirational words.
This could be, arguably, the most important day of your life.
Don't be nervous.
Don't be boring.
And don't forget the words.
After Simon's warning, everyone's on edge.
There's no turning back.
Your whole future.
this is it.
And as the first line takes the stage,
Jay Stone is confident because he knows being boring
is the last thing he has to worry about.
Jay, Jay, that was ridiculous.
Something's wrong with his microphone.
That is...
Next up is Lilly Scott,
a 20-year-old sandwich maker who caught the judges' eye back in Denver.
Okay, Lilly, you got four yeses, darling... well done.
Thank you so much, guys!
Since arriving here in Hollywood,
Lilly's been anxiously awaiting her moment in the spotlight.
I want to show everybody that I have what it takes.
It can happen in Hollywood.
Totally, it can happen here.
What's goin' on?
I'm doing, uh, Lullaby of Birdland by Ella Fitzgerald.
# guitar playing #
# have you ever heard #
# two turtle doves #
# bill and coo #
# when they love #
# that's the kind of #
# magic music we make #
# with our lips #
# oh, when we kiss #
# and there's a weepy #
# old willow #
# baby, he really knows #
# how to cry #
# well, that's how I'd cry #
# in my pillow #
# if you should tell me #
# farewell and good-bye #
# la la #
Well, Lilly, everything about you is refreshing.
I really liked you.
You're unique.
You did your own thing.
Very good.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
So what do you wanna do?
- Do you have a yes for him? - I have a maybe for him.
Okay, Sam, can you step forward, please?
Lilly.
You're the ones who've made it.
Congratulations.
So Lilly has reason to celebrate.
but for Jay, it wasn't the news he wanted to hear.
# p-ah-p-ah-p-p #
# peace out #
And outside in the lobby,
expectant father big Mike just got some huge news of his own.
how are you feeling?
All right.
This morning, I got a call from my wife.
She told me that she's starting to feel contractions.
She thinks she's going into labor.
Of course I want to be there.
It's my first child.
But I got a long week, and my wife wants me to succeed right now,
so... I gotta do it.
Michael Lynch has got a lot on his mind.
His wife could be having their first child any moment.
And he's gotta knock it out of the park here.
Let's see what he does.
I'm the next American Idol
because my wife is in labor right now with our first child.
And she wouldn't be happy
if I didn't come home with a victory this week,
- so... - That's big.
and also, I'll pummel anybody who disagrees.
# me and all my friends #
# we're all misunderstood #
# they say we stand #
# for nothing #
# and there's no way #
# we ever could #
# and now we see #
# everything has gone wrong #
# with the world #
# and those who lead it #
# just feel like we #
# don't have the means #
# to rise above and beat it #
# that's why we're waiting #
# yeah #
# ah, waiting #
# on the world to change #
# that's why we're waiting #
# waiting #
- # ah, waiting on the # - Thank you.
# yeah, yeah #
I thought that was good.
It was a good choice of song.
It was a good arrangement.
It was different.
Thank you.
Michael...
It's a good day.
So Michael and baby are on board for group day.
We'll check back tomorrow to see how it all plays out.
We have a lot more coming your way...
great performances and some dramatic cuts.
Stay with us.
More from Hollywood after the break.
Coming up, they shared their incredible stories
with the nation at their first audition.
When I step out on stage,
I'll just be thinking of how much I want to do my best for my family.
I was in a motorcycle accident.
The doctor said that I would never play guitar again.
I think it's a miracle that things happened the way that they did.
But what happens when Maddy and Casey hit the stage?
Casey, step forward.
Welcome back to day two of Hollywood week.
It's 4:00 p.m., and performances are in full swing.
Back stage is Justin Williams,
the cancer survivor we met in Boston.
# you know how I feel #
Thank you.
You know, I am gonna remember you.
Also waiting in the wings is Tim Irvin,
who had a shakier start in Dallas.
# so what happened to #
# bulletproof weeks #
# in your arms #
# and what happened #
# to feeling cheap radio songs #
Okay. Simon,
what do you think?
I think it was, uh...
probably not the best song choice in the world.
Yeah.
But I think there's more to come out of you, Tim.
I'm gonna give you another shot.
Now both guys take the stage.
First up is Tim.
Can he prove to Simon he was worth a second chance?
How y'all doing?
I will be singing David Cook's song, "Come back to me".
# you say you gotta #
# go and find yourself #
# you say that you're #
# becoming someone else #
He's got a good voice.
# to recognize the face #
# in the mirror #
# looking back at you #
# and so I let you go #
# I set you free #
# and when you see #
# what you need to see #
# when you find you #
# come back to me #
Thank you, Tim.
The chorus got a little shaky there, but other than that,
pretty good.
Thank you.
He's so serious, though.
Now it's Justin's turn.
Can this crooner continue to impress?
# fly #
# oh oh oh fly #
# in other words #
# I love #
# you #
# yeah, yeah, yeah #
- Thank you very much. - Yeah. It's a...
Thank you.
Jeez! It's crazy.
Uh, you know, definitely interesting.
Um... interesting.
That's all I'll say.
Thank you.
Decision time has come.
Justin, step forward.
back row...
welcome to the next round.
front row, you're going home.
So Tim moves on, while the journey ends here for Justin.
and as the sun began to set,
we had to say good-bye to more of the friends we made on the road.
like Paige Dechausse.
You just were all over the place.
It kind of didn't work that well.
And Erica Rhodes.
I think you have some work to do on your vocals.
I said I wasn't gonna cry.
um...
I know my folks would still be proud.
Jersey sisters Amanda and Bernadette were doubly convincing in Orlando.
Hollywood needs us, right?
The show needs us.
But, individually, they weren't able to deliver.
That was really strange for me.
I'm sorry, I just, uh, was not a fan of that.
They're my American Idols.
That's good. Thanks, Mom.
Thank you.
And back on stage is someone else who knows a lot about family support.
Hi, my name's Maddy Curtis.
We first met the 17-year-old in boston,
where she introduced us to her four brothers.
I think some people are a little skeptical of Down Syndrome.
Those four boys bring out the best in every person they meet.
When I step out on stage,
I'll just be thinking of how much I want to go out there and do my best for my family.
I like Maddy, dude.
I like Maddy too.
Welcome to Hollywood!
Well done, baby.
Thank you.
# when you're in my arms #
# I need no soft lights #
# if you'll only grant me #
# the right to hold you #
# ever so tight #
Thank you.
That was certainly the wrong song for you, Maddy.
Yeh.
Definitely, definitely, definitely.
All right.
Hopefully, I can do better next time?
We'll have to wait and see.
Thank you.
Next to take the stage is Casey James.
In Denver, he bared it all for Kara.
Personally, I say yes.
But that wasn't the only thing Casey wanted to expose us to.
My goal in this thing is to make it this the next round
so that I can really show you guys what's... what I do.
And what he does is play blues guitar.
# well, the doctor says #
# I need rest #
# all I need is her tenderness #
# put me on the critical list #
# when all I need #
# is her sweet kiss #
# he gave me #
# a medicated lotion #
# but it didn't soothe #
# my emotion #
# I don't need no doctor #
# comin' down with a misery #
Thanks, Casey.
Thanks, y'all.
Yo, dude, I actually loved that, and I loved the guitar playing.
It was really dope.
You really are a real singer-songwriter.
Thank you so much, man.
Now it's judgment time.
But if we don't, we're only gonna send two people home.
Okay, yeah, uh...
Casey, I had a...hmm.
Thank you, guys, all of you,
for coming and showing us what you got.
Casey, step forward.
Yes! Yeah!
Yeah!
So Casey moves on.
But the road ends here for Maddy Curtis.
Much like her Mom,
the judges must have thought Maddy simply wasn't ready yet.
After the break, it's the biggest moment in the lives of a waitress...
My heart is, like, beating out of my chest right now.
And a single Mom.
I'm doing this because I love my son.
He's the reason I'm gonna be the next American Idol.
Give him a better life.
But it's what they deliver onstage that will blow you away.
Wow, your voice is amazing.
It's 7:30 p.m. on day two of
Hollywood week, and over the past two days,
the stage of the Kodak Theatre has been riddled with drama.
You just failed the audition.
It's time to go.
to go, to go...
But the first round is nearly over,
and waiting in the wings is the last line of the day.
No turning back now.
Head out, go ahead, jump on the red marks, and good luck.
This is it.
In it, an emotionally fragile Didi Benimi, a waitress we met in L.A.
My heart is, like, beating out of my chest right now,
but I'm really excited that I did that.
You're going to Hollywood.
Welcome to hollywood, Didi!
But can she hold it together now that the pressure has doubled?
I'm gonna be singing Terrified by Kara Dioguardi.
And, heh... I've been working real hard at this,
and I think it's my time.
- Got it. - Yep.
# you by the light #
# is the greatest find #
# in a world full of wrong #
# you're the thing #
# that's right #
# finally made it #
# through the lonely #
# to the other side #
# you said it again #
# my heart's in motion #
# every word feels #
# like a shooting star #
# I'm at the edge #
# of my emotions #
# watching the shadows #
# burning in the dark #
# and I, I, I'm in love #
# and I, I, I'm terrified #
# for the first time #
# and the last time #
# in my only #
# life #
Thank you.
I hate to admit it, but I really liked that song.
- Really? You're lying. - I did, really.
I did too, I really...
Yeah, it sounded really current.
You're a waitress, right?
Yes.
I like the idea, somebody like you, waitress
of coming on a show like this, doing well.
That's what it's all about.
I thought that was terrific.
Thank you.
I think she's good.
I like that.
Also in this line is Chicago's Crystal Bowersox,
a single mom who's looking to make a permanent change in her life.
I am about to get a tattoo.
I'm really hoping that it's gonna be good luck.
Actually, I know it's gonna be good luck.
Here we go.
I'm doing this because I love my son, and I want his name on my back forever.
Look at this guy.
Look at that guy.
I can't be with him right now,
and I really, really miss him.
# Before the day I met you #
He's the reason I'm gonna be the next American Idol.
Give him a better life.
He deserves it.
# to my piece of mind #
# and you make me feel #
# you make me feel #
# like a natural woman #
# yeah #
# whoa, my baby #
# what you've done to me #
# done to me #
# mm, you make me feel #
# so good inside #
# good inside #
# oh, and I just wanna be #
# wanna be #
# close to you #
# 'cause you make me feel #
# so alive #
# you make me feel #
# like a natural #
# woman #
# you make me feel, honey #
Thank you.
I think what you have is that you're infectious.
People like you.
So you have a head start.
Uh, and you're real.
That was good.
Thank you.
You got mad love from your peeps over here singing background.
And now it's time for Crystal and Didi to hear the verdict.
Crystal, step forward.
Didi, step forward.
Front row, you're going through.
Back row, I'm so sorry.
So the single mother and the waitress are through.
Round one ends on a high.
I don't even know what to say, honestly.
I'm at a loss for words.
Well, 85 others will have plenty to say.
You're through to the next round.
Because this group still has something to believe in.
She made it too!
You're the ones who've made it... congratulations.
I'm just very grateful to have another day to try and get my... together.
What?
I think I might have just gotten an American Idol sign on my mouth,
and I'm very sorry about that, America.
- That is a wrap. - That is a wrap.
I made it. I made it.
I love you, daddy.
Tomorrow night will be the ultimate test for the contestants
who have survived the first cut.
It doesn't look great.
It doesn't feel good.
Do you not want us to be in the group?
Some will be victorious.
And others devastated.
You don't know what you're doing.
- That was a disaster. - Don't take anything for granted.
This is it for me.
Don't beg, it's not cool.
Because this is group round.
They stoled our idea...
And the results will shock you.
Don't panic.