Tonight on Idol, we reach new heights in the Mile High City
as Season Nine takes to Denver, Colorado.
Denver rocks! Whoo!
Prepare yourself as the altitude brings out the tension...
Please get that camera out of my face.
The terrible...
You just killed every cat in Denver.
and the talent.
# something kinda ooh #
Best voice today in Denver.
And watch out as one Denver contestant takes it to the limit.
Buckle up, because...
This is American Idol.
You all know this guy.
His band had 20 number one hits around the world...
Platinum four times over...
Safe to say, a household name.
# every time #
# you turn around #
# whoo-hoo #
Well, there was a time...
Let's call it September 2005...
when Chris Daughtry was just another face in the Denver crowd.
Four years later, that crowd has doubled in size,
making it twice as hard to get to Hollywood.
Yeah!
But these people were far from failing.
Oh, yeah, American Idol is mine! Boom!
Denver has the next American Idol, and it is Moi.
I'm the next American Idol!
No! I'm the next American Idol!
So they had the confidence.
But do they have the talent?
American Idol, Denver, yeah!
There was only one way to find out.
So we set up shop as the judges rolled in.
How are you guys?
Rejoining us on the panel,
Victoria Beckham.
Wow!
The altitude left the judges a little confused.
I thought this was Chicago.
No, it's Atlanta.
Austin.
Hi.
Kara, Kara!
Ha!
Not surprisingly, the girls were first to their seats,
giving Randy the chance to offer some insight on today's guest judge.
I actually like her.
Yeah, yes, you do.
You fancy her, don't you?
I think she's cool.
And listen, by the way, listen.
You know what someone said to me?
"I know Victoria's here,
but you're like the darker version of David Beckham."
I go, "I've been told that, yeah."
Literally separated at birth.
In your dreams, Jackson.
Mistaken identity was also an issue for
our first contestant of the day, Mark Labriola.
I probably get at least once a day that I look like Jack Black.
You know, I don't have a problem being compared with, like,
the ugliest guy in Hollywood,
You know, 'cause he's funny.
And I'm sure he gets girls.
So I deal with it, you know?
I am feeling stoked about today.
I mean, this is the day,
You know?
I'm the guy doing the thing that dude's do, and I'm here.
Hello.
Chello!
- Good, what's your name? - My name's Mark.
Okay, so tell me something interesting about you.
Well, I, uh...
I love cheese.
Yeah, what else?
Um, as a child, my mom took me when as a young kid.
We were kind of on the run for six years.
Yeah.
And I, you know, lived all over the place in tents
and cars and Hare Krishna temples...
On the run from what?
Um, well, my mom took me against the will of my dad.
And how old were you?
I was four years old.
So you're like a fugitive.
- Not good to be on this show, then. - Not a fugitive.
I think... wouldn't that be if I like escaped from prison?
I was like Harrison Ford or something?
No, but you were on the run.
Yeah.
Yeah, and did you get back with your father?
Yeah, my dad found me when I was 10
and brought me here to Colorado, so...
Okay, where did that leave your mother?
Uh, it left her in Maui, and, uh...
Maui?
You made it all the way to Maui?
Yeah, we lived in Hawaii,
and we lived in Alaska...
So she hasn't tried to get you back now?
I got a kid of my own,
so he lives with me...
You don't live with your parents?
No, you don't.
You're old enough to live on your own.
Exactly, yes!
What's happening here?
So your child is not in Maui now.
What are you doing, man?
My child's here in Denver!
Would you take your child to Maui?
Okay, that's it.
I would take my child to Maui.
I can't, I can't.
I would take my kids to Maui.
Let's take our kids to Maui.
Maybe we all could go to Maui.
What are you gonna sing?
I'm gonna sing " Tempted " by Squeeze.
Good luck.
Go ahead.
# I bought a toothbrush #
# some toothpaste #
# a flannel for my face #
# pajamas, a hairbrush #
# new shoes and a case #
# I said to my reflection #
# let's get out of this place #
# past the churches #
# the steeple #
# the laundry on the hill #
# the billboards #
# and the buildings #
# A memory of them still #
# keep calling #
Okay.
I was really surprised.
I mean, when you walked in, at first, I got a little bit angry
because I thought that you were kind of gonna do something quite jokey.
Yeah, I hate that.
Yeah, when there are so many people that come such a long way,
and those people are wasting time.
So that was a really nice surprise, right?
Yeah, and you were very, very honest about your background,
which I liked.
And he grilled you on the background.
Oh, yeah.
I do think you should go to Maui and meet your mom.
Well, my mom lives in North Carolina.
I thought she was in Maui.
Oh, god, please!
No, we lived in Maui,
and then...
Randy, yes or no?
- You didn't tell me that. - What is this, man?
You didn't tell me that.
What are we saying to this guy?
Yes or no, Randy?
I'm saying yes.
Victoria.
Kara.
100% yes.
Okay, you're through to the next round.
Welcome to Hollywood!
I'm confused.
Me too.
Really?
Yes! Whoo!
Oh!
Whoo!
Yeah!
This is for my little boy, Ian, and, uh,
also my mom who couldn't be here. Yeah!
I don't know, you know,
I thought my time was over.
You know, I'm, like, 28.
You know, I have a kid, and I just thought,
"Well, you know, my dream's done."
And, uh, I don't know.
That's not the case!
It's not over yet.
So that's cool.
Really cool.
Mark made it to Hollywood,
leaving a room full of people upstairs hoping they
just make it through the auditions.
Let's not forget, trying out for this show is a big deal...
the lights...
the cameras...
Him.
I'm kind of nervous.
You guys are awesome!
So it's only normal for people to feel a little anxious.
It's a big day for me.
And everybody deals with their nerves in their own way.
I have some xanax.
Some turn to a higher power.
Father god, you're...
And others try to hide behind costumes.
Some people have a nervous tick...
while others...
a queasy little laugh.
Meet Mario Galvin.
Hello.
Hello. What's up?
Oh, everything and anything.
How are you doing?
Your name is?
My name is Mario.
Mario.
Okay, and what do you do, Mario?
Uh, currently I'm working as a nicotine addictions counselor.
Okay, apart from that...
why are you here?
I'm here because I'd like to be the next American Idol.
Okay.
You have very white teeth as well.
What are you going to sing today?
I will perform Elvis Presley's " Jailhouse Rock ".
Right, okay, that's very brave.
Well, good luck.
Thank you.
# the warden threw a party #
# in the county jail #
# the prison band was there #
# and they began to wail #
# the band was jumpin' #
# and the joint began to swing #
# you should've heard those #
# knocked-out jailbirds sing #
# let's rock #
# everybody, let's rock #
# everybody in the whole #
# cell block #
# was dancin' to #
# the jailhouse rock #
Whoo!
Okay, what's the closest
you've got to getting a break?
Two years ago for a Broadway
Revue here, I got the role of
"Jekyll and Hyde".
And did that show actually
open?
That's a good thing.
No.
No?
Life goes on.
And there's always next year.
So never give up.
Coming up, Denver's talent dominate...
Yeah!
as many contestants are headed to Hollywood.
Welcome to Hollywood!
But Kenny's not going anywhere.
Kenny, you've got to leave.
I can't believe this.
Denver, Colorado.
A city known for the great outdoors.
Whether you come here for the cycling, the rafting,
or the skiing, there's one guarantee...
the air is always clean.
That is, until Idol shows up.
# 'cause I hate everyone #
# I hate everyone #
Get off!
Get out of here.
I'm gonna stick you.
Douche bag.
American Idol.
Kiss my...
Camera off me.
I'm a hateful person.
They keeping people who don't know how to sing.
They take me out in handcuffs like... like I'm a criminal,
like I'm a little...
Yeah, you...
What the... do you think they told me, damn it?
American Idol.
Please get that camera out of my face.
Quit talking to me.
Unh!!
Despite all that negative energy...
there was so hope in the
shape of our next contestant.
Meet Kimberly Kerbow and her five-year-old daughter Amelia.
My mom is Aamerican's...
next American Idol.
One more time, one more time.
All right, take two.
Amelia, say "my mom is..."
"My mom is..."
My mom is the next American Idol!
There you go!
Exactly.
Ready to do this?
Yes, I am ready.
What are you singing today?
"The way I am" by Ingrid Michaelson.
All right, let's hear it.
Go for it.
# 'cause I love the way #
# you say good morning #
# and you #
# take me the way I am #
# I'd buy you rogaine #
Okay.
# when you start #
# losing all your hair #
- Wait a minute... - Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You said "you'd buy him rogaine" and you looked at Simon?
I would buy him rogaine if he needed rogaine.
Don't you think he has thick,
lovely hair?
Kimberly, yes, thank you.
I don't think I need it quite yet, but thank you.
I didn't say yet, but,
you know, in a few years, it'll start...
Okay, right, okay.
Kimberly, have we met before?
Am I missing something?
It's like saying to someone "I'll buy you a wheelchair."
Yeah!
And a cane!
Okay, let's go back to you.
You're a single mom.
Yes, I am.
I wonder why.
Um...
Stop it.
Simon, that's not nice.
Simon, that's mean.
Kidding!
But you like Simon's hair, though.
It's... Of course I do.
I love his hair.
Good. Okay, Randy, yes or no?
Uh, I'm gonna say yes.
Oh, thank you!
Victoria.
I'm gonna say definitely yes.
Okay.
Kara.
I'm gonna say yes, too.
Oh, my god, thank you.
Kimberly, you're very lippy,
but you're very funny, and I'm gonna say yes.
Whoo-hoo!
Welcome to Hollywood!
Thank you so much!
I think you're trouble,
though, Kimberly.
Oh, no, I promise,
no trouble.
Look at me.
That's trouble.
We'll see.
Off you go.
Celebrate.
Welcome to Hollywood!
Thank you!
Go and talk to your ex.
Can't believe you said that.
That was funny.
Well, sorry.
That was bad, though.
No, but someone comes in and talks to me about going bald,
and you wonder why she's a single mom.
The irony was, I think she was wearing a wig.
No, she was not wearing a wig!
- She was. - She was. Because it won't be me, but I konw that.
Thank you.
She was wearing a wig?
Do you know why mom's so happy?
Because she's going to Hollywood!
Yeah!
# I'm a winner #
And Kimberly wasn't the only one headed to Hollywood.
As day one progressed, it seemed like everybody who
walked into that room heard the very same word.
Yes.
I'm gonna put you through.
Thank you, yeah!
Welcome to Hollywood!
Whoo!
The confidence the
contestants had shown may have been warranted after all.
Hollywood!
The judges were seriously loving the talent.
Wow.
God, we're putting 'em through, huh?
And our next contestant is hoping a golden ticket is also in her future.
My name is Danielle Hayes.
I'm 24 years old from Seattle, Washington.
And I host a live Karaoke, and do a little bit of
song writing and singing on the side.
I didn't exactly choose the easiest path.
It's really hard to make a living off of this.
And having a little three-year-old boy at home makes it even that much tougher.
# now I'm ready #
# to rise again #
So this would be an incredible opportunity to kind of
get to that next level so I can support my family.
Hello!
Hello.
How are you?
Oh, my God, I'm a wreck.
You nervous?
It's just, um... it's pretty crazy to be here.
And just watching everybody go through everything, it's just kind of emotional.
- Oh. - What do you do for a living, Danielle?
I host a live Karaoke,
and I sing in a cover band.
Wow.
Do you hate it?
Yes!
Why are you crying?
It's just been quite a ride.
Wow.
What do you mean by "quite a ride"?
I, um, decided a couple years ago to... to really start pursuing it,
and it's just... it's a lot more work than you think...
- It's hard. - when you got the dreams...
- It is. - so...
It's very, very hard.
A lot of bars, a lot of casinos,
a lot of corporate parties, and putting on a smile,
And...
But you're here today,
and this is your shot.
What are you gonna sing today?
I was gonna do "I'm the only one" by Melissa Etheridge.
Okay.
# and I'm the only one #
# who'll walk across the fire #
# for you #
# and I'm the only one #
# who'll drown in my desire #
# for you #
# it's only fear #
# that makes you run #
# the demon #
# that you're hiding from #
# when all your promises #
# are gone #
Thank you.
# I'm the only one #
I like you.
Um, but I think, for whatever...
I don't know what's going on in your life, but you're almost broken,
where you may have come in here just in time...
Yeah.
to rescue you from corporate hell.
Couldn't have said it better myself.
I don't think you've been allowed to be who you should be,
and I think you're a good singer.
For me, this was the most moving audition,
and what people look for when you're singing is to be moved.
Okay, Randy, yes or no?
I'm gonna say yes, 100%.
This girl's got a great voice and a bright future.
Victoria?
And I'm gonna say yes.
I think you're gorgeous, and I think you should take that little boy out
and celebrate with him, 'cause I think you're gonna go a long way.
I love that you wear your heart on your sleeve.
It's priceless.
And I'm gonna say 100% yes.
Simon?
And I'm gonna say yes.
Welcome to Hollywood!
Thank you.
I will not let you down.
Yes, Danielle, today is your day.
Yes!
# wanting more #
# before it slips away #
This opportunity means that it's not all in vain.
You know, maybe it's possible that I can really do this and that
I can support my son, and I can raise my son doing something that I love to do.
Still to come, the judges are looking good.
That is a photograph,
Not a drawing.
Yeah.
The talent keeps getting better.
Best voice today in Denver.
You're going to Hollywood!
And if you thought Simon was full of it, wait till you see these guys.
I'm a great singer.
Welcome back to Denver, baby!
The Denver talent has been impressive,
but it's not just the voices the judges have been noticing.
Yo, y'all look for me.
No, look for me.
Look for me.
Don't look for her.
With posh back on the judging panel,
It's more important than ever to come dressed to impress.
Hot dog in the house.
# fashion #
What I like about you is I think you do have natural style.
He's got a great look.
Yeah, a great look.
# fashion #
There's some funny hair going on here.
I love the fro.
# fashion #
She won me over with the boots.
I was like, "yeah, they're nice."
So you like the boots.
You like the eyes.
What did you like, Randy?
I actually like the voice.
Oh, yeah.
Casey James wasn't too worried about what he was wearing.
He was just happy being here.
When I was 21 years old,
I was in a motorcycle accident.
I remember thinking this truly is the end of my life.
It definitely changes you forever.
I had mutip-compound fractures in my femur,both bones and my arm and wrist
The doctor said that I would never play guitar again.
There's quite a bit of pain that I go through on a day-to-day basis,
but I think it's a miracle that... that things happened the way they did.
My whole goal in this entire situation is to make it to Hollywood,
because if I can just get there,
I really think I've got a shot, you know.
# it's not a silly #
# little moment #
# it's not the storm #
# before the calm #
# this is a deep #
# and dying breath of #
# this love that #
# we've been working on #
# can't seem to hold you #
# like I want to #
# so I can feel you in my arms #
All right, Casey.
This is a bad audition.
Yeah.
I disagree.
I totally disagree.
Really?
I like Casey.
Thank you.
I do.
No charisma, no effort...
But he's got a good voice.
He does.
Doesn't matter.
No, it does matter.
V, what did you think?
What do you look like with your hair down?
Cute.
He looks like a model.
You know, Simon, he's got a great look.
Yeah, a great look.
A great look, very handsome.
Wow.
You got to work on your personality 100%.
Absolutely.
I'm willing to do anything that I need to do.
Really?
Absolutely.
What about unbuttoning your shirt a little bit?
Take it off.
Take the shirt off.
Take your shoes off.
I mean, what are we doing here?
You got to see bikini girl.
Victoria, don't you want to see it?
For me, it was the hair.
What are we doing?
Say yes.
Personally, I say yes.
I say yes, because I do think he's got a good voice.
Randy, come on, dog.
Swing the vote, man.
Swing the vote.
Project runway.
Yeah, I know.
It's a different show.
Hey, you won't regret it.
You are when you watch this back, Casey.
This is really embarrassing.
This is the boys against the girls.
I'm gonna say no.
Kara, what are you saying?
I'm saying yes.
Yeah, I'm saying yes.
Randy, yes or no?
For the girls, 'cause maybe they'll prove me wrong later,
I'm gonna say yes.
You got another shot, but you do got to show...
You got to find some star persona, build something, dude.
I won't make you look bad, man.
I won't make you look bad.
I'm going nuts in my mind right now.
It's just insane.
I honestly never thought in a million years that
I would be able to make it to Hollywood.
Yes?
Hey, I made it to Hollywood.
So Casey had the looks and the talent.
While Tori Kelly had her very own fan club.
Are we interrupting a kindergarten class?
No.
These are all friends.
They're family friends.
These are family friends?
Yeah.
My name's Tori Kelly.
I'm 16 years old, and I'm from Canyon Lake, California,
and I'm a high school student.
She a good singer?
Mm-hmm.
American Idol is huge to me.
This is, like, at the top.
This is, like, crazy for me,
and I really want it really bad.
I'm gonna be on this show when I'm 16.
- You are? - Mm-hmm.
I'm gonna be really old when you're 16.
Yeah.
But Hope was more interested in meeting the judges
and made a beeline for the table.
Wow, is that for me?
Aw.
Wow, that is so cool.
Oh, Simon.
Why don't you give that to Simon?
- Wow, you're a good artist, aren't you? - You are.
You did these yourself?
- Kara. - Mm-hmm.
- You did this yourself? - Oh, how cute.
He lost his color.
You're a very good drawer.
That is a photograph, not a drawing.
Yeah. Simon.
Come on, hold it up.
Hold it up. Hold it up.
This is a photograph.
Yeah, that's not a drawing.
No, you're right.
Sorry, that's too accurate.
- That is real life right there. - Yeah.
- Hi, Hope. - Hi.
Listen, we love Hope, but we should get to...
Tori.
Tori, what's up, man?
You're gorgeous,
and that dress is gorgeous as well.
I love it too.
What are you gonna sing for us?
I'm gonna sing Gravity by John Mayer.
Okay, let's hear it.
# gravity #
# wants to bring me down #
# oh, twice as much #
# ain't twice as good #
# and can't sustain #
# like one half could #
# it's wanting more #
# it's gonna send me #
# to my knees #
- Thank you, Tori. - All right.
Tori. I really like Tori.
And you brought hope star in,
which is a definite plus in my book.
Hope is cool.
Well, if I'm being honest with you,
out of the two, I'd put Hope through.
- Oh. - Oh, no, that's ridicu...
Stop it. She's got a good voice.
Sorry, I don't think so at all.
I thought your voice was almost annoying.
Really?
- What'd you think, V? - Quite the opposite.
I mean, I love the way you look.
I love your turquoise.
- I love your dress. - Not a fashion show.
You look very...
It is about that as well, Simon.
It's about the whole package.
It's about star quality.
Voice is the important part.
You look classy.
Women are gonna like you.
You're really sunny, and that's great.
You're only 16?
You're like a human orange.
Let's take a vote. Randy?
- I'm gonna say 100% yes. - Oh, my goodness.
I love you... best, best, best voice today, definitely.
We have ended this audition day on a high.
- You're through. - Yes.
I'm gonna say no.
I think these three are mad, but there you go.
Welcome to Hollywood!
I'm so excited.
This is so amazing.
After our best day yet,
Tori is heading to...
Hollywood, Baby!
With 14 other contestants.
Can I keep this?
- You've gonna sign it? - Mwah!
I'm going to Hollywood, Baby.
Just say to...
Something like "my favorite judge."
I'm going to Hollywood!
"my favorite..."
- Sign it. - "judge."
That's very sweet of you.
Give me a kiss.
I'm going to Hollywood! Whoo!
Coming up...
It's Day two in Colorado,
and Denver goes the distance.
You flew 14 hours to make this audition?
As the talent reaches new peaks.
# ah #
You just killed every cat in Denver.
Welcome back to the second day
of auditions in Denver.
Denver rocks!
After an incredibly successful first day of auditions,
the crowds were still feeling nothing but confident...
- I'm good-looking. - They will love me.
I'm the cream of the crop.
I'm the creme de la creme.
And so were the judges.
Got a good feeling, a really good feeling.
However no one believes in
their own abilities more than this guy.
My name's Austin Paul.
I'm from Washington, DC,
and I'm a student at the University of Colorado,
where I study music composition and play football.
I'm a long snapper.
A long snapper is the guy that snaps the ball back,
hikes it through his legs back to
the holder for the kicker.
You know, my other teammates are jealous,
because I don't have to do that much,
and I still get fans and the joy and everything.
When I'm not playing football,
I sing all the time.
I sing on my moped.
Songs are coming to my head,
and I'll be like...
# do do do do do #
It's like, "wait. Who... did I just write that?"
I wrote down what I wanted to
accomplish before I died,
and number 42 was make it
to Hollywood on American Idol.
Wait, wait, wait.
42nd?
Well, what was his 41st?
I'm a singer, composer,
and I'm a football player?
# this is a call #
# to the color blind #
# this is an IOU #
# I'm stranded #
# behind the horizon line #
# tied up in something true #
# and someday I'll fly #
# someday I'll soar #
# someday I'll be #
# so much damn more #
# cause I'm bigger #
# than my body #
# gives me credit for #
Thank you. Randy?
Is that the way you normally,
naturally sing all the time?
Uh, no.
That's just one of the tricks up my sleeve.
Oh! Tricks!
- I like that. - Tricks.
Yeah, whoo! Yeah.
Right.
Kara, what do you think of the tricks?
You know, the whole grabbing his pecs
and the "bigger than his body" thing,
it was just... you come off a bit... cocky.
Sime?
Um, I think you could be very annoying.
Oh, my god.
It's one of those voices,
- after 30 seconds, you go, "oh, shut up." - Yeah.
I've just been there,
and that's the kind of voice you've got.
I mean, I disagree, but,
you know, you're the boss.
- For me, it felt a little bit arrogant. - Mm-hmm.
And like Kara said,
the lyrics... bigger than my body...
it kind of made me go, "no, don't."
I got a bit itchy from it,
cause I thought, "no, don't do it."
You should almost go the other way.
Okay, Randy, yes or no?
Dog, I'm gonna say no, Man.
I didn't quite get it, Baby.
- I didn't get it. - Kara?
- I got to say no. - Hold on.
And I think we're doing you a favor by saying no.
I think a guy like you needs to
be a little bit less confident.
I mean, I really think, like,
I could really be marketed well by you guys.
I think, Simon, I could make you money.
You could be the singing football player.
- No. - I think it's a great story.
- I mean... - It is?
We've already said it. It's a no.
It's a unanimous no.
- Okay. - I'm sorry.
Thanks for turning out, Man.
Take it easy.
I mean, even his sort of strut...
Yeah, no.
"Look at me. I am fine."
I'm shocked. I... uh...
I'm just... I can still be a star.
I think I still will be.
So it was back to the bench for Austin.
And just when we thought the confidence
couldn't get any higher in the mile high city,
24-year-old Kenny Everett stepped up.
I am the world's best singer,
for those of you that don't know me.
I consider myself the male Mary J. Blige.
I sing in the park around my way.
Everybody knows Kenny.
My singing is sort of a public service to others,
because it brings the community together.
I'm so ready to do this.
That's why I can't stay still, you know?
I'm so happy.
I'm ready to be the next American Idol.
Whew.
# call the radio #
# if you just can't be #
# without me, baby #
# hey-ey-ey-eeeyyy #
# ey-ey-ey-eyyyyy #
# yeah-eah eah-eah eah-eah #
# eah-eah eah-eah eah-eah #
# eah-eah eah-eah eah-hey #
# hoo-ooooh #
# ooh-ooh ooh-ooh #
# hoo-ooh-ooh ah-ah-ah #
# ah-ah ah-ah-ah #
# ooh! #
# and I just wanna be... #
Thank you.
# with you-ooh-ooh #
Thank you. That was catchy.
Yeah, we saw some gutsy and ballsy there.
It sounded, actually, like you'd been punched.
Um, and you were just screaming at us, Kenny.
I mean, it wasn't singing.
It was literally screaming at us.
Well, maybe I should sing something for you less...
Only one song today, Kenny.
Randy, yes or no?
Terrible. No, man.
- It wasn't good, dog. - Kara?
Yeah, I'm sorry to say, no, Kenny.
- Victoria? - I'm going to have to say no.
I'm sorry. It's a no, Kenny.
You gotta be kidding me.
- I'm a great singer. - No, you're not.
I've always been told that.
Kenny, you're not, and you never will be, honestly.
# no more drama #
# no more, no more #
# hey-ey hey-ey-ey-yeah #
# no more... #
Kenny, Kenny, Kenny...
# no more, no more #
- Kenny. - It's getting louder.
It's getting worse.
# go ahead, go ahead #
- Kenny. - Kenny, you've got to leave.
It's not getting better, dog.
I can't believe this.
Yeah, but I did like the choice of song.
- The choice... - Victoria...
It was a good choice of song.
I love Mary J.,
so I thought it was a great choice of song.
Kenny, you've got to leave.
# go, go, go #
- That's what I'm saying. - Yeah, go.
# go #
Yes, Kenny. The other way.
- That way, that way. - Sorry, Kenny.
- Excuse me. - Go, go, go.
Go, go out, go out.
Go, go, go.
So what has Kenny learned from this experience?
How can four people tell you
that you can't sing and you know you're a good singer?
Something has to be up with that.
Nothing.
# never knew what I was #
# missing #
But the community service continues
as he selflessly shares his gift with the world.
# ah ah-ah-ah ah ah-ah-ah #
But coming up,
the talent in Denver goes a mile high.
A million percent yes. I love this girl.
Whoo!
Plus, some of our most shocking auditions ever.
# yeeee #
Oh, god, I love this show!
Welcome back to American Idol.
We are 5,280 feet above sea level.
Looks nice enough.
But the mountain air is thin,
and so was the talent on day two.
# wha-ha- #
You just killed every cat in Denver.
# I had it all #
Nope.
# in a sad, sad #
# situation #
Was that in tune?
Relatively, yes.
# I had it all, baby #
They're a cruel bunch.
I didn't sing very well.
- I'm not gonna lie. - I did so bad, Mom.
Keep watching me till I cry?
# freedom... #
Freedom!
# whoo... hoo... hoo #
# freedom... #
# yeah #
# a little less conversation #
# a little more action, please #
# all this aggravation #
# ain't satisfactionin' me #
What about Vegas? Right?
It's a holiday, yeah.
# gonna ring once #
# sing out the phone #
# telling me know #
# you made it home #
What is...
Get me out of here!
It wasn't good, dog.
It was really, really bad.
Oh, god, I love this show.
Come on, that was awful.
Guess I just don't have what it takes.
# dit dit hey ee ee yeah #
Okay, do you know what?
It's like having Paula back on the show.
Oh, come on!
Where did all the talent go?
I'm the next American Idol.
No, he ain't.
There were still thousands outside
as Denver tried to go the distance.
All the way from Hawaii, baby!
Hey, we're from Texas.
We're from Walla, Washington.
But no one traveled farther than Nicky Nix.
At the moment I'm living in Florence, Italy.
And I traveled all the way from Firenze Airport
to Frankfurt, Germany, to Denver, Colorado,
For American Idol.
Music, growing up, was fun
because I didn't really know
that, that was gonna be something
I would end up doing.
I think, at a certain point,
I realized that was the only thing I really liked to do.
And... then here I am.
So, what... You've come a long way today,
Yeah, 14 hours you flew to get here.
So you flew 14 hours to make this audition.
- Yes. - Wow.
- I'm impressed. - Yeah, that is impressive.
That's dedication.
I flew from Florence to Frankfurt, Germany, to here.
Ask her if she's drunk any Helium.
- Why don't you ask that? - I didn't.
- Go on. - What?
Go on.
Victoria wants to know
if you've eaten any helium today.
- Pardon? - Nothing.
- What? - I just said... no.
Simon, come on!
- That is awful. - Come on, Simon.
- She's teasing. - You look beautiful.
- I like your dress. - Thank you very much.
What are you going to sing today?
Girls Aloud, "Something Kinda Ooh".
Good luck.
# something kinda ooh #
# jumping on my toot toot #
# something inside of me #
# wants some part of you... ooh #
# something kinda ooh #
# makes my heart go boom boom #
# something inside of me #
# wants some part of you... ooh #
# ooh... ooh... ooh #
# when tomorrow comes, baby #
# I won't even know your name #
# baby, so good #
# wanna follow on by #
# but I'll never meet ya #
# never see you again #
One of the most meaningful lyrics ever written.
- Better than... - I've got it... Yeah.
Every time I hear that lyric I almost cry.
Let's see the toot toot part.
You'r jumping on Simon's toot toot.
- I know. - Beautiful, beautiful.
You sing so much deeper than you talk.
- It's weird. - I've been told that.
I've a very high voice.
Yes, when you talk.
And then you sing, and it goes lower.
You're a funny little thing, aren't you?
- What? - I really like your attitude.
Um, I thought the song really suited your voice.
I thought you sounded great.
Yeah, and I like your look.
- You have beautiful skin. - Thank you.
All right, we're going to vote on you now.
Randy, yes or no?
A million percent yes. I love this girl.
- Good. Kara? - A thousand percent yes.
- Thank you. - Gone down a bit.
- Yes. - You've got four yeses.
You're going to Hollywood!
- Can I go out this way? - Yeah!
Grazie!
- She's cute. - Grazie! Mille Grazie!
Ma, I made it to Hollywood.
Oh, my god!
So Nicky's off to Hollywood on a high.
Coming up, she was a miracle baby.
I'm lucky to be here. I was two pounds.
Like, I couldn't even...
I couldn't breathe by myself.
- Can she work magic with the judges? - Right.
Is Hayley going to Hollywood?
It's 7:00 in the evening,
And the Denver auditions are coming to a close.
The thousands who arrived with so much confidence
Are now leaving, dejected.
I just don't wanna go home
and tell anybody that I didn't make it.
That's it. It's over.
In the face of so much disappointment,
Hayley Vaughan was trying to stay positive.
After all, she'd been a fighter right from the start.
I was born June 5, 1993.
Um, I was premature.
I was supposed to be born in August,
I was born in june.
And I fit in my mom's hand.
Two pounds.
I couldn't breathe by myself.
And I had a heart monitor.
So I'm pretty lucky.
I'm a miracle child. Hah!
When I was ten years old my dad passed away,
and that was really hard for us.
I loved being with him. And he always sang to me.
And so I think I got a little bit of my voice from him.
But we're getting through it. And now we're here.
And if he could see it, it would be so awesome,
'cause he'd be so proud.
My mom is so excited to be here.
She's wanted this forever too.
Like, she said that when she first saw the show,
she was like, "my daughter's gonna be on that,
she can do that."
I hope I can really pull through for my family
because we're going through a lot of stuff, you know?
So if I can be the first
black pop country kinda mainstream singer,
it would change my life completely.
# today I woke up #
# thinkin' about Elvis #
# somewhere in Vegas #
# I'm not sure how I #
# got here #
# or how this ring #
# on my left hand #
# just appeared outta nowhere #
# I gotta go #
# take the chips and the pinto #
# and hit the road #
# they say what happens here #
# stays here #
# all of this'll disappear #
# and I don't even know #
# his last name #
# my mama would be so ashamed #
- Okay. - Thanks, Haeley.
What do you think, Simon?
Cute little thing, aren't you?
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
You've got a slight lisp when you sing, you know that?
- Yeah... - Yeah.
I know...
What I like about you is that you're different, you know?
You're not coming in singing Mary J. Blige.
Therefore you stand out a little bit.
You obviously love that kind of music.
- And I think you're infectious. - Thank you.
- You've got a great smile. - Thank you.
I like you too.
You're so bubbly, which I think is great.
I love the way you're dressed.
You know what I like about you, Haeley?
There are not many black pop country singers.
Definitely.
So, that you have that dream, that's a big dream.
Yeah, I like that too.
I like that you're bold and you want to go there.
The only thing I would watch
is that you don't wanna get to
sound alike with Carrie and all of these singers.
She should start lower in her register too.
- I think you were a bit high. - A bit high.
That's what my sister told me before I came in here.
And I was like, "ooh!"
Where is your sister? She was right.
My sister loves you, by the way.
- She'd love to meet you. - Oh, really?
- Well, bring her in. - Really?
- Of course! - My sister and my mom.
- Can I bring both of them? - Yeah, of course!
Bring them all in.
You got any friends out there,
anybody from the mall we can call?
- Hello! - Hello!
What's up? What's up?
What's up?
- Nice family, nice family. - Beautiful family.
Is Haeley going to Hollywood?
As far as I'm concerned, it's a yes.
- Victoria? - That's only one.
- Yes. - Thank you.
- Randy? - A hundred million percent yes.
- You're going to Hollywood! - Welcome to Hollywood!
Maybe with mom and sis.
- That's so great. - Yeah.
Thank you so much.
Nice to meet you guys.
Welcome to Hollywood.
Whew.
Screams?
# and the world comes alive #
Day two saw 11 tickets fly out the doors.
Welcome to Hollywood!
Whoo!
I'm going to Hollywood!
From the mile-high city to a sky-high total of 26.
Hollywood!
And so that wraps up Denver...
well, almost.
In seasons past,
many contestants have tried hard to get noticed.
But only one has achieved the ultimate in notoriety.
Ha ha ha ha.
Last year, we gave you bikini girl.
The guys loved her.
Wow.
The ladies? Not so much.
How could anyone possibly go one better?
Aside from Kara, of course.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's the final contestant in Denver.
Prepare to meet...
No, really?
- Oh... - Come on.
What's the song? What're you singing?
I'm gonna sing, uh, Billy Ray Cyrus.
"Achy Breaky Heart"?
Of course, of course!
- Come on, bikini boy. - Here we go.
# you can tell my arms #
# to go back to the farm... #
I'm going back to Los Angeles.
- Bikini boy... - Don't move your hips like that, Honey.
- It's not a good look. - No?
- No. - It's bikini boy time.
Don't you want to finish? That's kinda rude.
I think you should, like, at least stay...
Kara, please stay. Can I get a hug?
They're coming back, right?
We... uh... well... bikini boy?
Are they really leaving?
Yeah.
Tomorrow night, we have one more stop for you,
and we strike goal.
It's the last audition episode before Hollywood,
and we are saving the very best for the very last.
One of the best 16-year-old I've ever heard.
Definitely one of my favorites.
Four yeses. Dude, you are going to Hollywood.
I can't believe this.
Join us tomorrow night as we end the auditions on the high.
I quite like that.