This week, our search for the next American Idol
brings us to the jewel of the midwest.
# this is #
# my kind of #
We're excited to be in the Windy City,
and we're blown away by the warm welcome.
Get this out of my face.
# my kind of town #
That is a joke.
# Chicago is #
You think I playing ?
# my kind of people who #
They suck.
This place. Goodbye.
American Idol.
Kiss my...
This is American Idol.
Get out my face.
Chicago-style.
We started things off here back in season one.
And we came back in season five.
Now it's season nine, and we're set to do it all over again.
Welcome to Chicago!
They were glad to see us back in the Windy City...
We love it when American Idol comes to Chicago.
And since this is the hometown of our nation's president,
they gave us a welcome fit for...
Well, you know...
a president.
Where we are met with cynicism and doubt,
we will respond with that timeless creed
that sums up the spirit of a people...
Yes, we can.
His influences have been felt all over the country,
and today many of the idol hopefuls
are following in his footsteps.
Yes, we can!
Yes, we can.
He's my main man.
Hopefully, the next idol will be from Chicago,
and this could be the new sign.
I may not be Obama...
but he's the next American Idol!
So far, this is our largest stop on the audition tour.
And we're hoping that somewhere in this sea of
12,000 candidates we find the one person we're looking for.
I believe I have what it
takes to become America's next top model.
Idol!
I mean... I mean... I mean America's...
Now that we know where they stand...
It's time for the idol candidates to move inside...
and deliver.
I'm Chicago's finest.
And to make sure of that...
The judges arrive in Chicago hots on the audition trial.
Yo! Party people!
And speaking of hot,
our guest judge is country music superstar...
# let's go, girls #
Shania Twain.
Oh, yeah!
I love Shania Twain.
She has penned some of the greatest pop songs.
She's like a pioneer,
And now I'm gonna go and stalk Shania Twain.
Having sold over 65 million albums,
Shania has changed the face of music as
she successfully crossed country with pop.
And she won five grammys for her efforts.
# man, I feel like a woman #
This is a once-in-a-lifetime chance
for so many of these people.
Honestly, I think I'd pee myself
if I was really standing here for real.
I did do that once when I was younger.
Good thing Simon is here to comfort Shania through her childhood trauma.
I'd be bored without you.
He even tries to brighten her day.
By the way, can we get some light in here?
It's like being in a bunker or something.
Is there a reason why we have to sit in the dark then?
Thanks to Simon, things are properly lit.
The cameras are rolling,
and now the judges are ready for
the first contestant of the day.
My name is Caitlin Upperly.
I am 19 years old, and I'm from West Des Moines, Iowa.
My mother has been trying to talk me into trying out
for American Idol for a really long time.
I always just was kind of standoffish about the idea,
But some thing's happened this summer
that changed my way of thinking.
For the last, um... few months,
our family has kind of been broken up.
My, um, husband decided to divorce and just...
rug kind of pulled out from underneath us, so...
it's been really hard for all of us.
My parents have gone to all of my performances
and everything since I was very young.
And this is the first one that they, you know,
that they're not here together.
She's doing this, in part, for me, I know.
This day could be a new chapter in our lives,
and especially for Caitlin, so...
we're excited to see what happens.
- Hello!  - Hello.
- Hi.  - How are you?
Very good.
Very nice to meet all of you.
Thank you. What's your name?
- My name's Caitlin.  - Caitlin. Okay.
And why did you enter the show this year?
Well, I'm doing it because
I've a lot of family problems at home, so...
Like what?
Um, like my dad leaving my mother.
So it's her favorite show, and it's kind of...
Who are you siding with?
What are you doing, man?
I mean, I'm kind of forced to side with my mom,
but I'm still speaking with my dad.
Simon Cowell, therapist hour!
What are we doing here?
You feel better off after that conversation, don't you?
It's like the air's now cleared.
Yeah, it's all out in the open now.
Part of the reason why I'm here.
Okay, and what are you gonna sing?
Syrup and Honey by Duffy.
Yum!
Sounds good, right?
# don't you be out #
# all night long #
# leaving me all alone #
# because I #
# need your love #
# don't you be usin' #
# every day #
# workin' away #
# because I... I... I #
# need your love #
- Thank you.  - Shania.
I think your voice has a lot of very interesting qualities
and I just thought it sounded very unique.
Yeah, what I really like is
you don't sound anything like Duffy
cause we've had so many sound-alikes
that come in here and sound like Duffy and Adele.
But I think that there's something there.
Kara.
Yeah, I do see potential in you, you know?
You're a pretty girl.
But I'd like to see you do something a little perkier,
a little more energetic.
Okay.
Yeah, it's all a little bit the lights are off.
- But somebody's home!  - Yes.
The lights are dim.
Like the room we walked into today...
Had to sort of open the curtains and...
I think you have a voice that could sing a hit song.
I think.
Okay. Kara, yes or no?
- Yes.  - Randy.
- Yes.  - Yes for me too.
You got four yeses.
Welcome to Hollywood!
Thank you so much!
- Awesome.  - Thank you. Thank you so much!
Well done.
We're going to Hollywood!
Yay!
Looks like Day One in Chicago is off to a good start.
Love you.
Love you too, mom.
Coming up...
The season nine talent keeps getting stronger.
Four yeses.
Welcome to Hollywood!
Yeah! Chicago shows her personality...
Whoa! Ow!
And is this guy for real?
Oh, come on, Brian.
Welcome back to American Idol.
Before we get back to the auditions,
we thought we'd allow one of the city locals
to tell you a little bit about a few of
the names of this great city.
Chicago has rarely been the same place twice.
It's been the Windy City, the Second City,
the city of big shoulders,
player with the nation's railroads,
candy capital of the world.
My kind of town, city in a garden, chi-town, Chicagua.
Whatever you wanna call it.
Me and nearly 3 million others call it home.
Those are a lot of names to live up to.
Back at the auditions.
And just looking to make a name for herself,
is 26-year-old Broadway baby Amy Lang.
I'm auditioning for American Idol
Because I figure if all I have to do is
wait in a line for a couple of days,
to be famous and make my dreams come true.
It's worth it.
If someone were...
to write a music about me,
it would probably be called Amy Lang,
Amy Lang, Amy Lang...
The musical! Yeah!
I'm excited to meet Ryan.
Tell me something...
Cause we have, um... we have a history.
# always thinks of you #
Me and Ryan secretest...
hot item.
- You look good.  - Thanks.
Just a little shorter than I remember you.
- Remember me?  - He was the first celebrity
that I ever had an inappropriate dream about.
- And how did the dream end?  - Good!
Why don't we send you into the audition.
I'm happy you ended that... in that way.
Oh, my god!
- Hello.  - Hi! How's it going?
You guys look good.
So do you.
- Oh... Stop!  - Oh!
I like her.
- I like you already.  - You're funny.
You can do something with your boobs, it says here.
I'm gonna do it during the song... just wait for it.
- Yeah, I'll make it happen.  - Can we sing?
What's going on up here, man?
Sing? What are you talking?
Is this a singing show? Nobody told me.
What you singing?
Dr. Feelgood, by Aretha Franklin.
Okay. Freaking out.
We got it.
# don't send me no doctor #
# fillin' me up #
# with all those pills #
# I got me a man #
# named Dr. Feelgood #
# and yeah #
# ooh #
# that man takes care #
# of all my pains #
# and my ills #
# good god all mighty #
# the man sure makes me #
Got it, got it, got it, got it, got it, got it, got it.
- I actually thought she fainted.  - Where's the boob thing?
Oh, just a little...
- Whoa!  - I was busy singing.
It wasn't as big as it usually...
You wanna be careful with that.
We do it to the beat too,
like... # good god almighty #
# the man sure makes me feel #
Oh my god!
Whoa! Talent.
Randy, she's boob-boxing.
Boob-boxing... yeah.
Boob-boxing.
She's boob-boxing.
Musical boobs.
Nobody else.
- Just me.  - I'm gonna say no, Amy.
Really? Even though I can sing?
Yeah, they're not gonna go to Hollywood.
I can sing things more serious too. I was kinda having fun with it, but...
It was just too funny of an audition...
Couldn't really take it seriously.
- That's it. It's over.  - Simon.
That's it. That's it.
You gotta move on.
- Okay.  - Thank you, Amy.
All right, thank you.
Bye, sweetheart.
I should have sang something serious,
but I thought it was so fun...
that it would stand out and they'd enjoy it,
- They'd laugh.  - I just wanted to make myself stand out.
And what'd they call your... move?
I don't know. I call it the boob flex.
That's the first time we've seen that.
What are you gonna do?
And so farewell, America.
Ba-dump-bum!
Amy didn't get the support she wanted from the judges,
but her family was there to give her a lift.
And as with many contestants who audition...
I'm here to support.
Knowing that family and friends have their backs goes a long way.
# long as we got each other #
- Next Idol, right here.  - She's really good!
- And I'm good.  - That's Emily!
And with her family set by her side,
our next contestant hopes she will make the cut.
My name is Charity Vance.
I'm 16 years old, and I'm from Little Rock, Arkansas.
I live with my mom and my dad.
They have a salon. It's in our house.
Vance Salon. This is Charity.
Both my mom and my dad,
they've been doing hair together for like 20 years,
and the clients are really encouraging.
They always want me to sing for them,
so it's really fun, and I get to practice performing.
We've been watching American Idol
since she was eight years old.
Every Tuesday night,
we'd have friends and family over to the house and,
I mean, it's like a party at our house.
If I get that golden ticket, I am going to freak out.
I will be a crazy person on American Idol, like...
I want it a lot!
Yeah, yeah.
- Hello.  - Hi.
Okay, what are you going to sing today, Charity?
- Summertime.  - Okay.
# summertime #
# and the livin' is easy #
# fish are jumpin' #
# and the cotton is high #
# well, your daddy's rich #
# and your ma is good-lookin' #
# so hush, little baby #
# don't you cry #
Thank you, Charity. Randy?
Wow. I was really impressed.
I didn't know really what to expect.
I mean, small voice, but very interesting sound.
I liked it.
I was pleasantly surprised.
And you're using your range.
You're not afraid to do it.
You probably have to hone in a little bit more
on the better qualities of your voice.
But she has a lot of personal style, I would say.
Mm-hmm. That was a great version.
Thank you so much.
Yeah, I've heard that song a lot.
What I liked about it, Charity,
was it was unique to you.
Yeah. Mm.
On record, you sound great.
I gotta tell you.
Okay, Kara, yes or no?
- Yes.  - Randy?
100% yes.
- Shania.  - I say yes as well.
Charity, full house. You're through.
Welcome to Hollywood, Charity, Charity!
- Awesome.  - Well done, kiddo.
She made it her own.
Can't believe she's 16!
So let's see what happened here...
Simon said yes! Simon!
Come on!
I'm going to Hollywood! Whoo!
That's my little dance.
Whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop!
So Charity snags the second gold ticket in Chicago.
Hollywood!
And as she twirls her way to Hollywood...
we had to break.
Coming up...
more incredible performances.
You singers like you is why I like doing this show.
As Chi-town feels the pressure.
Out my face.
Plus, it's Angela Martin's last chance.
I can't give up... until I touch my dream.
Does her journey end in Chicago?
Find out what happens after the break.
Welcome back to American Idol
and welcome back to Chicago.
Since the break, things have taken a turn.
# my name is kelly #
# ke... kelly #
# kell... kell #
# my name is kelly #
# ke... kelly #
# do you hear my name? #
Dude, no, no.
And all of the characters have started to come out.
How are you guys?
Causing the judges' patience to wear thin.
# I am the crazy #
# accordion lady #
# this is my song #
Maybe this next batch of contestants will cheer them up.
# give 'em the old #
# three ring circus #
# hi #
# ah #
# ma #
No.
# stun and stagger them #
That wasn't serious, was it?
# how can they spot #
# you got no talents? #
# Here's a hero #
# it's not unusual #
# to be loved by anyone #
# can you feel #
# the love tonight #
Do you enjoy giving people pain?
I'm a high-pitched singer so...
You shouldn't even be doing that.
# razzle dazzle 'em #
# and they'll make you a star #
# ah #
This is a complete and utter waste of time.
All right, thank you very much.
Okay, so that didn't help.
While the judges take a much-needed break...
Not really great ones today.
The affects of the afternoon slump can be felt all around.
- Out of my face.  - They suck.
That is a joke.
So far, only four golden tickets have been given away.
And the excitement that was experienced earlier
by contestants going to Hollywood...
Aw.
has been replaced by tears and the sounds of disappointment.
I'm not coming back.
And as Simon heads back from the break...
He was wrong about Jennifer Hudson.
He's wrong about me.
he has to handle some unfinished business.
- Simon.  - Oh.
How could you say such awful things about my daughter?
So you're not happy with me?
Hell to the no.
I was giving your daughter good advice.
I do not agree with you.
Try to be mad at me, but you do agree with me a little bit.
I've always liked you.
But now I don't like you anymore!
You know you still like me.
And our final contestant of the day is 28-year-old Angela Martin.
She's auditioning for a third time
And has some unfinished business of her own.
The very first time I auditioned, uh,
shriners hospital saw me on American Idol
and they agreed to take care of my daughter till she turned 21.
And it's a blessing.
# we climbed down #
# the mountains #
But after my audition, my dad was killed.
I had to go to Hollywood a week after his funeral.
# oh-oh-oh #
He was planning on coming to hollywood with me.
It's all over.
After being cut in Season 7,
Angela came back in Season 8,
making the top 50 only to face another setback.
Last year, you couldn't make it to one of our shows.
- Mm-hmm.  - Tell us why.
Well, I had a traffic violation... a warrant.
Had to leave and take care of that.
- You had a court date.  - Yeah.
I've seen a lot of dreams die.
But I will never give up.
I can't give up until I touch my dream.
I remember this girl.
Yes, I remember Angela.
Come on in, man.
She looks great.
You look great.
Angela Martin.
So you made it to Hollywood last time, right?
I made it to the top 50 and I had a warrant.
And I had to drop out.
- Naughty Angela.  - Traffic, though.
- Not that bad.  - Speeding.
You need to slow it back a bit.
- Yeah.  - All right, so what you singing today?
Just Fine by Mary J. Blige.
- Do it.  - Okay.
# let it go #
# can't let this thing #
# called love get away #
# from you #
# feel free right now #
# go and do #
# what you want to do #
# can't let nobody #
# take it away from you #
# from me, from we #
# no time for moping around #
# are you kidding? #
# and no time #
# for negative vibes #
# 'cause I'm winning #
# it's been a long year #
# I put in my hardest #
# gonna live my life #
# feels so good #
# to get it right #
# just fine #
- Ah, yeah.  - Good choice of song too.
Nice too 'cause she's been through it.
Yeah. You have the right attitude and it shows in your voice.
It's people like you...
Singers like you why I like doing this show.
Because you're really talented.
You need a break. And you're just good.
Thank you.
Yeah. You're good.
You're good. And you try, try again.
This is what I really like about you.
You actually listen to the criticism,
and you take it in, and then you show up and you're better.
- And you do deserve a break.  - Definitely hot vocals.
Very good audition. Let's take a vote.
- Kara, yes or no?  - Definitely.
- Simon.  - No.
- Kidding!  - Yeah.
It's a yes.
- Shania.  - Yes for me.
Yes for me. Welcome to Hollywood!
Welcome back, baby!
Angela's back. She's back.
Pay your tickets, girl.
Pay 'em. Pay them tickets.
Don't have that happen next year.
Go slower.
How many times would this be?
- This would be the...  - she's great.
- Try, try again works.  - She's great.
When you're good, try, try again works.
So how's this chapter gonna end?
Hopefully with my daughter getting everything
And me just continue on doing what I do.
You guys... you guys have me in tears now.
I'm going to Hollywood again.
Again again. Again.
The storm is over.
- Over.  - Over.
And so is the drought.
It wasn't easy, but seven other contestants from day one
will be joining Angela in hollywood.
Through to the next round.
Welcome to Hollywood!
And for these contestants and their loved ones...
It doesn't get any better than this.
- Nick, four yeses.  - Whoo!
Welcome to Hollywood, Nick.
Mom, I just wanted to call
and let you know I'm going to Hollywood.
Yeah, Chicago!
Yeah!
Yes!
Up next, the day two auditions begin
and Chicago reaches for the right notes.
Maybe we should give her the note.
# and I #
Okay, okay, okay.
Welcome back to Chicago, where day two is about to begin.
Here in Windy City, we've seen the largest audition crowd of the circuit.
I would say it's almost like a million people here.
More like 16,000.
And with such big numbers come big dreams.
I'm the next American Idol!
I am it! I'm number one. Whoo!
And even bigger expectations.
She can sing her behind off.
I'm gonna be the next American Idol.
Yeah! Yeah!
And despite a poor showing on day one,
the judges' hopes are still magnified.
This is town of big talent, Ryan.
Jennifer Hudson. Kanye.
Hopefully today, man, Chicago will show improvement.
Come on, Chicago.
And as everyone settles in for the big day,
will the first contestant, 26-year-old curly newborn, measure up?
- Hello. How are you?  - All right.
- And your name is?  - Curly.
And what are you going to sing today, Curly?
Today I'm gonna sing Maxell, a woman's work.
Aw.
- Y'all ready?  - Please.
# oh-oh-oh-oh ooh ooh ooh #
# pray god you can cope #
# I stand outside #
# this woman's work #
# now starts the craft #
# and the fa-wa-ah #
# I know you got a little life #
# in you yet #
# I know you got a lot #
# of strength in you #
Okay. Yeah, dog, it was...
You have a high voice.
The high voice and the whole thing with the woman's work...
Okay, I don't know what that was.
- Oh, god.  - Yeah.
Do you find when you sing at home,
a lot of animals turn up outside the house?
Stop it. Stop it.
And it takes days to finish a song.
He just has a high voice. He has a high voice.
- High?  - Oh, the Chicago skyline's so beautiful.
All right, Curly, that's right.
We weren't expecting a high...
Thanks a lot.
Not the start we expected for the day to auditions here in Chicago.
We haven't said yes or no.
- I guess it's no.  - It's a no.
- No?  - No?  - No?
- No.  - No.  - Yes.
- No.  - No.
Curly's high notes didn't quite hit the mark.
Maybe next time.
Well, until then, 19-year-old Alana Halbert
is picking up right where he left off.
# I think of you #
# every step of #
# the way #
- Here we go.  - Should I keep going?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You should've started lower, maybe.
Bring the chorus down and then start the chorus.
- Okay. Um...  - Maybe we should give her the note.
I'll cue you in. Let me cue you in.
# and I #
Oh, oh, okay, okay, okay.
A singing lesson, season 9.
- This is wild.  - It's getting worse.
That was your $10 singing lesson.
Okay, it's a no for now, sweetheart.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you. Take care.
- No.  - Aw.
Aw. Why'd they say no to you?
Why do you think?
Um, I don't know, they said...
I don't know, actually.
I was kind of just, like, dang off and...
I didn't know what they were trying to say,
like, you know what I mean?
I had no idea what was, like...
I... I really had no idea what I was doing so...
They told me, uh, I don't really remember, actually.
- Um, I don't know.  - Did you have fun?
Yes, I had fun. Thank you.
But if Alana wasn't clear on what happened
inside the audition room...
It was black and white to the rest contestants
throughout the early morning auditions.
They go in...
And they come out...
Without a golden ticket.
Hoping to add some color to the morning is our next contestant.
Yoo... hoo... hoo!
Sir, my name is Brian Kraus.
I'm 27. I'm from Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.
I was in the army.
I was in Korea.
Being in the army's very depressing.
So they need some form of entertainment,
some type of morale.
I used to sing for the troops.
I was told not sing in uniform.
And, you know, I couldn't help it and I got in trouble.
Screw you, Sergeant Hart, I'm the next American Idol.
Hi. Hi. Good... good afternoon, Ma'am.
- Your name is Brian?  - Yes.
Okay, anything we need to know?
I'm gonna be doing, uh, uh,
one of my favorite artists today, Tiny Tim.
Oh, okay. Any... any time you're ready.
# tiptoe to the window #
# by the window #
# that's where I'll be #
# come tiptoe #
# through the tulips with me #
# oh, tiptoe #
All right, okay. Okay, Brian.
Brian, is this a joke?
No, it's not a joke, Ma'am.
And... and do you tiptoe like that?
Ask anyone from grade school till... till current.
Yes, I do, ma'am.
Brian, swear on your mother's life that was not a joke.
Uh, yes, Simon, I'm gonna swear on my moter's life that is not a joke.
That is my singing voice.
Well, okay, well, then I guess we have to analyze that.
Brian, it was not good.
That was weird.
That was weird, right?
Uh, Mr. Jackson, I was shooting for Tiny Tim today.
What do you mean shooting for Tiny Tim?
- Uh, Mr. Cowell...  - oh, come on, Brian.
Please don't call him Mr. Cowell and Mr. Jackson.
I apologize, Sir.
Brian, we're just gonna... we're just gonna leave this.
Yeah. Brian, no.. Thank you.
Tiptoe that way.
# tiptoe by the window #
To be honest, it was a very long process today.
I feel exhausted.
So I feel like slipping into a warm bubble bath
and just relaxing my thoughts.
# oh, tiptoe #
# by the gardens with me #
Brian's audition left the judges asking
the age-old question "real or fake?"
My question is why are there no golden tickets,
nobody jumping up and down, no tears of joy?
We'll be back after this.
After the break, she beat the odds once already.
I had a really bad asthma attack
And went into anaphylactic shock.
But what are her chances of making it to Hollywood?
And the guest judge gets technical.
You have a beautiful bottom end and...
- Huh?  - Whoo whoo.
Welcome back to Chicago.
It's 12:00, and the day two auditions are moving full speed ahead.
Whoo!
Inside, the awaiting contestants are all pumped up.
Yeah! Oh!
- Those are good.  - Talking to him.
But with no golden tickets so far,
the judges are looking for a real contender.
I usually say yes, but this time I have to say no.
Okay. They just might find it
in Chicago's own Harold Davis.
Ow! I have spirit.
I have soul.
I have everything that I need,
you know, to be the greatest.
This is my life.
I'm tired of eating microwave dinners.
I want to eat steak.
# trying hard now #
I'm gonna do things I didn't even know I can do in there.
I'm gonna hold notes as long as I can possibly can.
# ohhh #
I'm willing to fight for the glory of being on American Idol.
When I walk into the judges' room,
I'm gonna shoot off like a rocket.
I'm gonna blast off in glory.
# ohhh #
I'm gonna show them I'm the best.
The champion is here. The champion is here.
# oh oh oh #
- Your name is?  - Harold Davis.
Okay, nice to meet you, Harold.
Nice to meet you too.
What are you gonna sing?
- Usher, nice and slow.  - Okay.
# lady #
# Would you mind if I #
# and take it nice and slow? #
# Slow, slow, slow, slow #
# Ooh, yeah #
# I'm talking to you, lady #
# would you mind if I #
# and take it nice and slow? #
# Oh oh oh oh-oh-oh #
# It's 7:00 on the dot #
# I'm in my drop-top #
# cruising the street #
# I got a real pretty #
# pretty little thing #
Okay, okay, got it, got it,
Got it, got it, got it, Harold.
Thank you. Right, Kara, yes or no?
In terms of your vocals,
They're not where they need to be.
- Okay, Randy, yes or no?  - No.
Yeah, dog, it's a no.
You're not up for this.
No, I just got allergies,
'Cause my allergies is acting up.
No, it's not allergies.
Harold, for now, it's an absolute no.
It wasn't a great audition, I promise you.
I'm not being mean. It wasn't great.
Oh, Harold. Aw, Harold.
Oh, dog, it's not the end.
Don't cry.
Harold, come on.
- Chin up.  - Dog, it's not the end, man.
You made it to the audition.
That's a good look.
You learned a lot from us, hopefully.
You can take that and work on it, dog.
Work on it and come back.
Not even the champ was a match for our panel today.
Sorry, Harold.
It's early afternoon, and so far, there's been little reason to celebrate.
This is the longest it's been, ever,
this season without any golden tickets.
So you guys all feel confident you'll get one?
Yep.
Well, she'll have to impress the judges first...
Something that's been difficult to do
since we've been in Chicago.
# Baby, I'll try #
# to love again, but I know #
It's like Shania's song...
That don't impress me much.
# That don't impress #
# me much #
# oh #
# so you... #
God!
# ah #
# how did you get here? #
It's just not... it's not... No.
# oh oh oh #
You'll never, ever make a living out of singing.
# ah-ah-ah #
I'm sorry.
Baby, that was bad.
- I'm sorry.  - No.
A no for now.
Thanks.
We're trying to be too kind because they're so bad.
I know, I know, I know.
Hoping to make a good impression is our next contestant.
My name is John Park.
I'm a student, but I could be the next American Idol.
When I was a senior in high school,
I dicided to apply for voice program in college,
my parents were very against it at first,
because, you know, they wanted me to have a job when I graduated.
I come here today
because I just feel like music is the only way
that I can truly express myself to people.
# If I ever leave you, baby #
# you can say, "I told you so" #
# and if I ever hurt you #
# you know I hurt myself #
# as well #
# I love you #
# more than you'll ever know #
Thank you very much, John.
- Shania?  - I was very surprised.
And, yes, you have beatiful bottom end.
Huh? What?
Why, thank you.
She's right.
- Why, thank you, Shania.  - She's right.
- You have nice lips.  - Thanks.
- Shania, what's going on?  - I'm flattered.
Lips and a bottom end... what is going on?
Yeah, I mean, you made the bottom-end thing.
- I mean the voice.  - I... no, I...
You have a nice tone down there, okay?
Down there? What are we doing here?
- Randy...  - You're attractive!
Okay, anyways, no, I was very pleasantly surprised,
And you have a good head.
And you...
Well, now you've got me thinking.
I didn't even do anything.
Somebody save me.
Anyway, I think you have a nice voice.
These are dangerous. Be careful.
I agree with Shania. I was also very surprised.
I didn't know what you would sound like,
and I think you have a really good voice.
And I would say yes.
- Randy?  - Yes, I like John.
- Shania?  - Yes.
- Well, obviously. Uh, it's four yeses.  - Oh. Thank you so much.
- This is a dream come true.  - Welcome to Hollywood, John.
Thank you so much.
There's gonna be a lot of people screaming in about a second.
Watch this.
Finally, finally!
I'm gonna be very careful of my choice of words.
I don't think you are gonna regret what you want back, Shania...
It just all went on a roll there.
I have no regrets.
Shania loved me.
She said... she said really...
Oh, my goodness.
Are you surprised?
- Yeah, a little bit.  - Yeah?
All four of them said yes.
Now, what do we do to celebrate?
So a very happy John Park is the first winner of the day.
And we're gonna take a break and come back
and see if the golden-ticket streak
can stay alive right here in Chicago.
Stay with us.
After the break, the touching story of Paige Dechausee.
They said she had a 30% chance of surviving.
And she's still here.
She's beaten the odds with a second chance at life,
but will the judges give her a chance in Hollywood?
We're approaching the end of two long days here in Chicago,
and as the last of our 12,000 empties in the stadium,
the reputation of the city's talent falls on the shoulders
of a small handful inside the holding room.
This is the group right here that has not had a chance
to see the judges yet, but they're excited.
Are we gonna find the next idol here in this group today?
There's been a shortage of golden tickets so far today,
so we're expecting a lot from this small group right here.
Hoping to breathe new life into the judging room
is 21-year-old Paige Dechausse,
and she's brought a few supporters along for the ride.
The whole family's here.
We came up in a limo.
Grandma Roxy got us the limo today,
And we all squeezed in.
So we're looking forward to a happy ride home.
As a kid, I had asthma and was in the hospital a lot,
and when I was 15, I had a really bad asthma attack
and went into anaphylactic shock,
where your throat closes up.
I was in the studio where I was singing at the time.
We were in a lesson, and next thing I knew, I passed out.
When we got to the hospital,
They actually called us into a back room
and had the grief counselor there.
And they said she had a 30% chance of surviving,
and if she did that she would probably have brain damage.
I told my husband, "I want her music and her earphones.
It's the only thing that's gonna keep her going."
And we did that.
And she's still here.
- All right, what you singing?  - Sam Cooke,
- A change is gonna come.  - Do it.
# I was born by the river #
# In a little tent #
# Oh, just like the river #
# I've been running ever since #
# It's been too hard livin' #
# And I'm afraid to die #
# It's been a long #
# A long time comin' #
# But I know #
# A change gonna come #
# Hmm, yes, it will #
Thank you.
All right, what'd you think, Simon, of Paige?
Okay, a little bit indulgent, I thought...
All about you singing to yourself almost.
Yeah, I thought the vocal was pretty good.
You just had some pitch problems in the beginning.
It got better towards the end.
Let's take a vote. Simon?
- No.  - Shania?
I'm not entirely convinced, but for now,
I would say... I'll say yes.
I see potential in you.
I'm gonna say yes.
She needs a chance to show us what she has, I think.
Come on, look at her.
- What's going on here?  - Let's get him, let's get him, shania.
- What's going on here?  - Please?
She's cute, and she's good.
She can do it.
Because she knows...
I'm a blubbery mess.
She seems to know what she wants.
Yes, she's just got to work...
She didn't put her personality into her vocal,
and I think she needs to work on that.
I mean, you've heard so many...
You realize here, you have Shania Twain,
one of the greatest to ever do it, here,
trying to convince me that you should go to Hollywood.
I think she has potential.
Come on, Randy, please.
She seems humble.
She's got her head on straight.
She wants to do it.
She's attractive.
Yeah.
Randy.
Okay.
Welcome to Hollywood!
I think I can't be surprised.
We got you.
It's an overwhelming moment for everyone.
That's what...
That was... that was...
You just got "girlified."
Didn't see that one coming.
We have seen only, maybe one other today.
Tell me how it feels to have the other one.
I don't even know.
Breathe, breathe.
Give me a second.
As Paige takes it all in,
She's thankful for her family's support and overcome with emotion.
I'm so happy, I can't even describe it.
The last thing I wanted to do was walk out to all these people
without a golden ticket, and I did it.
Ah, it'll be a good ride home in the limo.
And as our time here in Chicago comes to a close,
The last few hopefuls vie for a golden ticket of their own.
# why does it hurt #
# so bad? #
# you hurt me so bad #
# baby, you're all #
# that I want #
# when you're lying here #
# in my arms #
# I'm finding it hard #
# to believe #
# we're in heaven #
# and I'll be #
# you're crying shoulder #
# I'll be love's suicide #
- I'm gonna pass. - Okay.
I say yes.
I'm gonna say yes.
I'll give you one more chance...
Welcome to Hollywood.
Finally, finally!
Oh!
Marcus, you got four yeses.
You guys for real? Oh, my god!
Welcome to Hollywood, Marcus.
Finally the dream has come true.
Yes, I'm happy.
Welcome to Hollywood.
You got four yeses!
- Hi, mom?  - Yeah?
I made it to Hollywood.
See you in Hollywood.
Golden tickets were hard to come by...
But the grand total for Chicago was a lucky number 13.
I'm going to Hollywood!
# go, Ryan #
I'm going to Hollywood.
Whoo!
I'm the next American Idol!
Yes, we can!
In all, 12,000 hopefuls descended upon us,
and after two days of grueling auditions,
We now say good-bye to the Windy City.
We're out. That's it.
- That's Chicago.  - That's it... Chicago.
Nice to see you.
Thanks for hanging with us.
This was fun.
And it's safe to say we walk away with Chicago's finest.
And for the ones who made it...
Yes, we can!
Yes, they did.
We're going to Hollywood!
# when you wish #
# upon a star #
Tomorrow night we'll be coming to you
From Orlando.
But this ain't no sing-along.
Welcome to New Orlando!
American Idol, baby!
This is where dreams can come true.
Competition is fierce, as we continue our search for
the most talented singers in America.
- Brilliant.  - You're so genuine.
Whose dreams will become reality?
Yes!
And who will come apart at the seams?
- Ow!  - Ow.
My pants feel ripped.
You see me fighting for this show,
and then you're gonna kick me out like that?
You don't want to miss this.