August 28, 2009.
Space Shuttle Challenger blasts off from the Kennedy Space Center in Florida.
And hoping to launch themselves into orbit are 10,000 Idol hopefuls.
Will they shine like the stars they're reaching for?
American Idol, baby!
Whose dream will become a reality?
This is Orlando...
And this is American Idol.
Welcome to Orlando.
They say it's the place where dreams come true.
Cause you always have to have a dream.
I'm gonna be a star.
But for this massive 10,000 hopefuls,
their dreams lay in the hands of our four judges...
who were not there.
While the crowd waited for their shot, Randy, Simon,
and I were approximately 235 miles away in Miami,
Taking a well-earned break, obviously.
After some R&R, we all needed some serious TLC
as we boarded a plane to Orlando.
Oh, my god!
Here we go.
At least Kara...
Hi, guys.
And our guest judge Kristin Chenoweth...
Magic doors... They just open for you.
had arrived.
And the two seemed to really hit it off.
I'm already digging this girl.
Let's go rock it.
Come on, let's do it.
As the BFFS headed for a touchup, we arrived a touch under the weather.
You don't look as tired as you thought... Don't worry.
Hello.
He's not tired.
This is Orlando.
Not at all.
But ever the professionals, as the line filed in,
we took some questions from the local press.
These guest judges... What do you think of these, uh...
Who have we got today?
He doesn't actually know who we have today.
That's true. She's actually a really big deal.
She's known as a darling of the American musical stage.
Now fresh off her stint on the Fox hit Glee...
Kristin Chenoweth's talents are are taking her from strength to strength.
This year, she put an Emmy on her mantle... right next to the Tony.
With such a busy schedule, we were lucky to steal her away for a day.
I'm very nervous and excited.
I'm not nervous for myself.
I'm nervous for the kids.
But nerves were not an issue for Theo Clinton.
Have you ever thought about being a superhero?
Um... I'm super at whatever I do.
I am beautiful.
I am all that anyone could be.
# I feel pretty #
# oh, so pretty #
# I feel pretty and witty #
# and bright #
My gift is something that you get only on particular days.
I'm just something that you can just get a piece of on Monday
and then on Tuesday where you put in a microwave and warm
it up... it's still good.
I am the next American Idol.
And if I'm not the next American Idol, I am gonna be in the bottom three.
Theo, what's up, man?
Theo!
Whoa!
Oh, my.
Theo, what's going down, man?
Good evening.
Good evening. Yes.
It is daytime, the sun is out, but good evening.
Assuming, unlikely, that you won,
Where would you see yourself in ten years' time?
In ten years' time I can see myself running a corporate salon.
So you wanna... Hair dressing salons...
Yeah.
And a recording career.
I also want to be a musical artist.
So you can sort of bob in and out.
I wanna be a fashion designer... I wanna do it all.
Greedy.
What you gonna sing, man?
Pat Benatar, Heartbreaker.
Great.
Go for it.
# your love is like #
# a tidal wave #
# spinnin' over my head #
# drownin' me in your promises #
# better left unsaid #
# you're the right kinda #
# sinner #
# to release my inner fantasy #
# the invincible winner #
# you know that you were #
# born to be #
# you're a heartbreaker #
Whoo!
# a dream maker #
# love taker #
# don't you mess around #
# no no no #
Wow!
Wow, you got some power.
You feel good after that, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah, I could tell.
You released a lot of stuff.
Yeah, I was working hard for this, cause I know how Mr. Simon is...
Mr. Simon thinks you're gonna be on your way to your hairdressing salons, Theo,
- because it won't include singing. - Oh.
I mean, you screamed the song at us.
I can do Whitney Houston, I Believe In You And Me.
No.
Nothing else is going to help you, theo, and part from...
Luther Vandross, Dance With My Father.
When you walk in like that, I mentally said no.
# back when I was a child #
And cut.
It's not that you're even pitchy.
It's that the tone of your voice...
It's so over the top and just not good, sweetie.
Well, look at Jennifer Hudson... They had to work with her.
Honey, you're not Jennifer Hudson.
Randy, yes or no?
No, Theo, baby, it didn't work, man... I mean, it all doesn't work, man.
- Kristin? - Not for this, but... Not for this.
It's a no.
- But come here, let's say hello. - Okay.
I'm sorry, honey, really.
It's just... It was too over the top, babe, really.
You don't need to wear all this.
I'm fine, I...
Yeah, Theo, you don't need these outfits, man.
- Come on, lose all that, man. - Good luck.
You're better than that, and you smell nice.
Oh, poor guy.
Turn left, turn left, turn left.
No, wrong way, sweetie.
Wrong way.
It's...
Honey, back here, through
the... You gotta go through the...
- No, wait. - That way.
- Oh... - No, that way.
Oh, God, I mean it's so... No, no.
- Are you his... - Friend.
We're all friends.
You're buddies.
Um... you could say we're like best friends, cause I'm his assistant.
Theo.
I didn't make it.
Now, Theo...
Well, come here, Theo.
Theo.
That was so fun.
That was really fun.
Okay...
I still have life, health,
and strength, so I'm not that down.
I still have my birthday's tomorrow.
I'm gonna celebrate my birthday.
Happy birthday... What do you want for your birthday?
Thank you.
I wanted to go to Hollywood, but I guess I'm not gonna make it this year.
You should get down that one or you wanna keep that one on.
I guess I'm not gonna make it this year.
Well, nice to meet you.
Thank you, Mr. Ryan Seacrest.
It was nice to meet you.
Sorry it didn't work out.
I gotta go wash the glitter off my hands.
We'll be right back.
Coming up... Their stories will inspire you.
My son is diagnosed with autism.
My whole life growing up as a kid,
I wasn't able to use that side of my face.
I spent four birthdays behind bars.
Their voices will amaze you as Orlando delivers some outstanding talent.
Best I've heard this whole audition season.
But not everyone is headed to Hollywood.
You sang as if you sat on a cat.
And they are not pleased.
No, you see me fighting for this show,
and then you're gonna kick me out like that?
Welcome to the sunshine state!
The Orlando auditions were in full swing as 10,000 hopefuls take their shots in front of the judges.
Barring a liberal smattering of pixie dust,
the morning has proven to be far from the fairytale.
It was a no.
Unfortunately not, guys.
Didn't make it.
Aw!
The contestants are starting to grate on Simon Cowell.
Kara and Kristin, on the other hand, are having a ball.
The ladies had made a pact at the top of the day.
I need all the girl power we can have here on this thing.
And all that power wasn't helping the mood of a road weary Simon Cowell.
# blame it on the girls #
# blame it on the boys #
I'm so happy to be sitting by
Her.
This is so fun.
Whatever they did, they did it together.
Cool!
They had fun together.
I think you're so cute.
Are we crushed out on him?
He's 21!
They endured the horror together.
# we are #
# the champions #
Oh, my God, okay, okay, stop, stop.
But most of all, they annoyed the out of Simon Cowell.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Can you hit a note like that?
Yes!
Yes! Yes!
I think we're too loud for Simon.
No!
Simon, are we bugging you?
No, I just have a little headache today.
But it was the contestants who felt the pain as Orlando hit a rough spot.
You walked in with the lights off.
Nope.
I was actually beginning to fall asleep.
Aw!
You walked in like a cocktail stick.
And then sang as if you sat on a cat.
I mean, that was the audition.
# blame it on the boys #
The lack of golden tickets only added to the pressure on
the contestants in the holding room, and for Seth Rollins,
there was already a lot on the line.
I'm married, I have two kids... A son who is almost five.
His name is Samuel.
And a daughter who's nine months old.
Her name is Faith.
My son is diagnosed with autism.
He's a great kid.
He's awesome.
But there are, you know,
difficulties that come with that diagnosis
and just everyday life and things that you don't even notice.
How about that one?
Yay!
For families that have autism it's really tough.
A lot of the marriages end in divorce.
As a man, you know, I wanted to feel like I could fix things.
Um...
but you can't fix things.
There are things that we would like to do for our son...
it's hard to afford right now.
Um, but we'll certainly, you know... that would be such a blessing,
to be able to afford everything and get the best care for him that we need.
Ready?
Okay.
Go!
To be able to do music full-time is just a dream.
And I'm just so excited to have this opportunity.
I love you.
- This is so cool. - Can we go get presents?
Yeah, we're gonna get presents.
Like a golden ticket.
Can I have a present?
Stay out here.
You stay out here.
No! I wanna go with you.
Wait...
- Is this mom? - I wanna go with you!
You know mom?
No! I wanna go
with daddy!
Oh, baby, it's okay.
Yeah, yeah.
So how old are you?
I'm 28.
So this is your last chance.
My last chance.
Um... Is singing your dream?
Uh, my family is first and foremost, but I love to sing.
I would love to have a career in music, and I am just so excited to be here.
What you singing, man?
Gonna sing Someone To Watch Over Me, Frank Sinatra.
Wow, okay.
# there's a somebody #
# I'm longing to see #
# I hope that she #
# turns out to be #
# someone #
# who'll watch #
# over me #
# yes #
# like a little lamb #
# who's lost in a wood #
# I know I could #
# always be good #
# to one who'll #
# watch #
# over me #
# oh #
Thank you very much, Seth.
What do you think, Kristin?
Well, I like the fact that you took a Gershwin song from
many, many years ago and made it your own.
I like your voice.
I like everything about you.
I wanna keep hearing you,
And that's really the best compliment I can pay somebody.
Thank you.
Simon?
Good. Yeah, I like the fact you know who you are, Seth.
Good choice of song.
You got a good voice.
- Just need to exert a little bit more... - Okay.
- Exude some more... - Animation.
- Okay. - Vibe, you know, a little bit more energy, a little bit more performance.
Let's take a vote.
Yes.
Yes. Kara?
Million percent yes.
Simon?
That's an easy yes, Seth.
I say yes too. Four yeses.
Welcome to Hollywood!
- Yeah, baby. - Yay!
He is great. I loved him.
Beautiful voice too.
Nice tone.
Amazing.
To have four yeses, I think should, you know... for him,
- give him the confidence that he really has something special. - Dad's going to Hollywood!
Yay!
# and I will try #
# to fix you #
What color are daddy's shoes?
White.
What color is Samuel's hair?
When we come back...
The dream turns into a nightmare.
# rollin' on the river #
Oh!
My pants done ripped.
What?
Kara gives a serious wake-up call...
You think you're a great singer?
As our most dramatic episode unfolds.
You see me fighting for this show, then you're gonna kick me out like that?
As we know, millions of people flock to Orlando to reach for the stars.
Our contestants were aiming just
as high as the auditions continued.
# when you wish #
# upon a star #
American Idol would change everything.
# makes no difference #
# who you are #
What?
# anything #
# your heart desires #
You're great.
Thank you!
Please.
- One song, please? - Jordan...
- It's not gonna help. - I'll prove it to you right now... One song.
Jordan, Jordan, it's a no.
I'll be back next thing... You'll see me.
I bet you you'll see me.
I don't think you're quite ready yet.
Oh, come on, please.
# too extreme #
# when you wish #
Thank you, ryan.
# upon a star #
# your dreams #
# come #
# true #
Maybe some magic would come to Germaine Purefoy
who's back for a second chance.
I auditioned for American Idol back in season seven.
It was kind of a road trip.
Bunch of guys got together in college.
I didn't make it.
I wasn't surprised.
I kinda deserved it.
And my feeling was it just wasn't meant for me at the time.
So I was thinking that I need to give this another shot.
But it all comes down to this day, and I think that today
potentially my life could change.
Yo, yeah, come on in, man.
I have no force of coming in.
- Don't be scared. - Is it my turn?
- I'm scared. - What are you gonna sing?
Uh, Tony Bennett.
Oh, great! Okay.
# you light up your face #
# with gladness #
# hide every trace of sadness #
# although a tear #
# may be ever so near #
# that's the time #
# you must keep on tryin' #
# smile #
# what's the use of cryin' #
# you'll find that life #
# is still worthwhile #
# if you just smile #
Thank you very much, indeed.
Aw...
Uh, you know, what I really like is how pure of a sound you have.
It's so seamless.
I never worry once when he goes up for anything high.
There's no strain.
I mean, I love you.
I think for me...
the best I've heard this whole audition season,
it's my favorite... dude, I was blown away.
I was really impressed.
Thank yo so much.
You know, and the other thing is, of course you have a great
voice, but you're like... it's honest.
I believe it, and I'm listening to every word,
and I'm hanging on every word.
'Cause I really believe that you mean it.
And you got a nice smile.
Yeah, you do.
I thought that was a good choice of song for you.
I think the chicks will like you.
Uh, let's take a vote.
Simon, yes?
- Yes. - So yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Two bazillion percent yes.
Welcome to Hollywood!
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Germaine, you got something to smile about.
I'm not typically a risk-taker.
I play it safe all the time.
So the fact that, you know, I'm holding this in my hand right
now just lets me know I think that
I should start maybe taking a few more risks, you know.
It works. It works.
It's 7:00 in the evening,
and our holding room is now an empty shell... leaving just one
contestant alone with her thoughts.
You're the last of the day.
Oh, I am.
You are the last of the day.
Dead last.
My name is Shelby Jessel.
I'm 18 years old from Avon Park, Florida, and I'm a waitress.
When I was born, my seventh cranial nerve was undeveloped.
So my whole life growing up as a kid, I wasn't able to, you know,
smile correctly or use that side of my face, which is the right side.
You've always liked performing in front of people?
A little uncomfortable.
But it looks like you function fine.
Really? Well, thank you.
So... but that's been something that has been an insecurity, I guess.
Yeah, definitely.
It's been hard.
When it comes to chasing your dreams and going after what you
wanna do, you just kind of have to set that to the side and do it.
I'm so nervous, but I'm trying to like calm down,
and I just can't find a good way to calm down, and I don't know.
This whole thing is kind of intimidating to me,
and I'm just kinda like...
- take it easy, you know. - Yo.
I'm your last one.
Hi, Shelby.
Hey.
Why are you here, Darling?
I just graduated high school,
and I really just wanted to do something out there.
And I love singing.
Everyone's persuaded me to do it, and so... here I am.
Okay, and what are you gonna sing?
Turn Me On by Norah Jones.
All right, good luck, Shelby.
Okay.
# like a flower #
# waiting to bloom #
# like a light bulb #
# in a darkened room #
# I'm just sittin' here #
# waitin' for you #
# to come on home #
# and turn me on #
# my poor heart is #
# gettin' so dark #
# since you been gone #
# but... #
Oh, my god. Holy.
I am so sorry.
Oh, my god.
I love that. That was awesome.
That was the best part of your audition.
That was great!
I'm so sorry.
You know what, Shelby, we can judge you on up to that.
I like you.
But I wasn't blown away with your voice, no.
I actually kind of liked your voice.
- I thought the voice so cool. - Really?
And I actually liked that you were kind of afraid of us.
We looked like we were kind of afraid of you.
Really?
And then you broke open the ice, and we were like, yo!
That's our girl right there!
Now we're friends.
Yeah.
I guess.
I think you have a good potential.
And you're 18, and you have a lot more growth to do.
But I think you have something there inside.
Oh...
Simon?
With a small "y", yes.
I'm gonna say yes.
Randy?
I'm gonna say with three big letters, yes.
Oh!
Welcome to Hollywood! Yeah!
Shelby joins 18 others to make it to Hollywood from day one.
You got four yeses,
Sweetheart.
Whoo!
I'm going to hollywood!
# well, i'll be back #
# welcome back #
# in 15 minutes #
# well, I may be a superstar #
# welcome back #
# in 15 minutes #
# I won't forget who you are #
I'm going to hollywood!
More auditions from Orlando,
tomorrow, day two.
Congratulations, darling.
Yay!
Coming up... Orlando's talent keeps getting better.
Brilliant.
You can really, really sing.
Are you serious?
A unique performance puts the panel...
No.
Come on, Randy.
And Cornelius...
Ow!
Splits his pants.
I would do more moves, but...
No, no, no, I don't want
you to move at all right now.
Stay right there.
No more moving.
Welcome back to Orlando.
It's day two of auditions...
This is where dreams can come true.
And everyone was hoping for more magic like yesterday.
Kristin had been called back
to New York, so today there
would be no guest judge on the panel.
It gives us more quality time to bond.
seriously Randy? And that was Kara plan with the contestants.
Just go for it.
If you have fun, we have fun.
And that's basically the way it is.
And that was advice Jay Stone certainly took to heart.
How's it going?
Yo, come on in, man.
Yeah, you ready?
I've been ready.
I am so ready.
So you know what it is.
You watch the show.
You ready for this?
This is the dream.
Absolutely.
What you singing, dog?
Come together by the Beatles.
Do it.
# here come old flattop #
# he come groovin' up slowly #
# he got joo-joo eyeball #
# he one holy roller #
# he got hair #
# down to his knee #
What?
# one thing I can tell you #
# is you got to be free #
# come together #
# right now #
# over me #
Oh, god.
All right, nice.
That was like a crazy roller coaster ride.
Nice, nice.
You know what?
That was pretty amazing, though.
You know, Jay, I'm actually soaking wet after listening to that.
That makes two of us, man.
Seriously, I feel like I've taken a shower.
Oh, my god.
I'm gonna say yes.
That was hilarious.
Hm?
That was amazing.
Do you actually sing?
I do, yeah.
# ain't no sunshine #
# when she's gone #
Anywhere, he could be booked.
# dee dee dee dee #
# it's not warm #
# when she's away #
# ain't no sunshine #
# when she's gone #
# and she's always gone #
# too long #
# anytime she goes away #
# wonder this time #
# where she's gone #
Okay.
Okay, so it's a no.
Boo. No!
Yes.
- Yeah, no, - come on.
What are we doing here?
Oh, come on, he's a...
You know what?
He's a good singer.
Skibbety skibbety bop.
Come on, yes.
Skibbety skibbety boom.
Yes.
All right, well, let's take a vote.
Let's just see how much more you've got.
- Sim, yes or no? - No.
- Kara. - I say yes.
Why?
I don't know.
I think he was a good beatboxer.
He's got a good voice
when he stopped acting like a human drum machine.
Come on, Randy.
You know you want to see that in hollywood week.
I do?
I'm bringing something new and different that this
competition has never seen before.
There was a guy a couple years ago who was a neat beatboxer.
Blake Lewis.
He wasn't doing what I'm doing.
He wasn't singing and beatboxing simultaneously.
Okay, Randy, yes or no?
Yes.
Randy.
Come on, Randy.
I think Simon was like a
And Kara was like a...
And now Randy's like a...
Uhh!
Yes, yes.
Drum roll.
I love this.
Okay, okay, okay, okay,
Okay, okay, okay, okay, yeah.
Randy apparently is a...
Whoo!
# Stand up #
# and break it down #
# Come on #
# bring that beatbox back #
# so do you feel it? #
Even though she was outnumbered, Kara stuck to her guns
and Jay Stone was off to Hollywood.
There was just time for a quick celebration in the holding room,
And the party was on.
# Yeah, you know #
# that you want it #
# 'cause you can't deny it #
The girls of Orlando were more than happy to get their dance on.
But could they sing?
# There is a house #
# in New Orleans #
# that they call #
# the rising sun #
# take me on a trip #
# I'd like to go someday #
# Take me to New York #
# I'd love to see L.A. #
# they say we're lovers #
# kept under covers #
# I just ignore it #
# but they keep saying #
# we laugh #
# just a little too loud #
Okay.
You're cute, and I like that little rasp in your voice.
Yeah, I like that too.
Good.
Thank you.
There's something infectious about you, you know what I'm saying?
You've got all this bubbly vibe and all of that.
- You're going to Hollywood. - Are you serious?
Welcome to Hollywood,
Brittany Starr!
It's okay.
I'm proud of you.
So they had the voices and the moves.
But if you want to talk flexibility, talk to Cornelius Edwards.
So where did you learn to dance?
Well, I have friends that are adult entertainers and things of that nature.
No.
What kind of entertainment?
Well, they dance, like, uh,
for money, I would say.
Like, they're entertainers.
Are you saying, Cornelius,
They shed their clothes for money?
Well, if that's what you want to call it, yeah.
They dance for money.
What dance did they teach you?
Oh, okay, we've got it, we've
Got it, we've got it, we've got it.
What are you singing, man?
Rolling by Tina Turner.
Okay.
Do it.
# Big wheel keep on turnin' #
# proud Mary keep on burnin' #
# and we're rollin' #
# rollin' #
# rollin' on the river #
Ow!
# doo doo doo doo #
# doo doo doo #
My pants done ripped.
What?
Ow!
Your pants split?
I felt that. God!
Oh, oh, I can't look at that.
My problem is I need to go to Hollywood.
I'll tell you what.
I'm gonna have to say yes after that.
Thank you.
I mean, seriously.
That's the best thing I've ever seen.
I'd be more worried about the trousers when you go.
I mean that is sacrifice.
I would do more moves, but...
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, no more splitting.
No, I don't want you to move at all right now.
Yeah, yeah, stay right there.
No more moving.
I can't...
Yes?
I can't.
Yes for me.
Yes or no?
Yes.
Three yeses.
Welcome to Hollywood.
Get some new pants.
Go get some new pants.
No, no, no.
Just get some new pants and leave.
Get a towel so you can wear it out.
What happened, buddy?
I'm going to Hollywood.
You're going to Hollywood!
Whoo!
Congratulations.
Come on, that was hilarious.
I've never seen that before.
The pants splitter.
That was hilarious.
Go on and get my jacket, please.
Megan, Megan, he's not gonna show his split.
His pants have ripped.
We're gonna go to a commercial break and
let the kids continue to watch this program.
Disgusting, these producers.
Coming up, some of the best talent yet.
Welcome to Hollywood!
Yes!
Will these two sisters be torn apart by Hollywood?
Sister in blue, yes.
Sister in yellow, no.
And the audition that ends in disaster.
You can't sing, Dude.
Are you serious?
How are you?
Hi, Handsome.
Welcome back to Orlando.
How do you do?
I do fine.
I'm good. I'm excited.
Yeah?
I'm so excited.
I'm excited.
I'm Bernadette Disimone.
I'm 27.
I'm Amanda Disimone.
I'm 23.
And we're sisters from Cherry Hill, New Jersey.
We live in the same house with our mom, and in the house,
there's a salon.
We're down here a lot.
We make people look beautiful and we have a lot of fun here too.
A little bit.
No!
Come on.
It'll grow.
From when we wake up in the morning, it's a performanc that's going on.
There's always a performance.
# we're sisters #
# and we live together #
# won't this be a cute picture #
Love you, sis.
She has the talent to go all the way.
That's nice.
Thanks.
She stinks.
No, I'm just kidding.
Now say something good about me.
Ah!
Hi.
They come in twos.
Yes, we do.
Sisters.
Who's the best singer?
We're equally great.
Who's gonna go first?
Um, if you don't mind, sis, I'm oldest.
I'm supposed to stand to the side.
Wherever you'd like.
It's your show, honey.
Get it, girl.
# oh #
# oh, baby, oh, baby #
# don't you leave me this way #
# you're the meanest old thing #
# that I ever did see #
# I guess if you say so #
# I gotta pack my things #
# and go #
# that's right #
# and hit the road, jack #
# and don't you come back #
# no more, no more #
# hit the road, jack #
# and don't you come back #
# no more #
Okay, thank you.
Sis number two, please.
Little sis.
All right.
# I need a man #
# who'll take the chance #
# on a love that burns #
# hot enough to last #
# and when the night falls #
# my lonely heart calls #
# oh, I want to dance #
# with somebody #
# I wanna feel the heat #
# yeah, I wanna dance #
# with somebody #
# yeah #
Hmm.
# with somebody #
# who loves me #
Hmm.
I love her.
Yeah, you guys love each other, huh?
Yeah, you... you're kind of judging each other.
Are you from Jersey?
How did you guess?
Was it the hair?
Oh, yeah. I don't know.
Something about something that told me you were from Jersey.
"Joisey."
They're from Jersey.
"Joisey," yeah.
Randy, what do you think?
Uh, I actually think you picked the better song.
Hit The Road Jack was a little easier to sing.
You picked a really tough one.
I don't know.
- Interesting. - I kind of like something about them.
They look a little like they...
they could really bring something to Hollywood week.
Thanks, Kara.
I think we can, for sure.
We're it.
We're ready to work.
- We want it. - Work.
Simon?
I mean, your crazy nodding when you were listening to your
sister, like Whitney's been reborn, or like...
Yes, yes.
She hasn't.
Okay, Randy, yes or no?
Uh...
Please, Randy.
Yeah.
Hollywood needs us, right?
The show needs us.
Kara knows.
She's like, "yeah." Oh!
We can't go back out there and look my mom in the face.
Uh, I'm gonna say yes to the sisters.
I'll give it... shh!
I'll give the sisters one more shot.
Kara?
How do you break these two up?
Oh!
I know.
I'm gonna say yes.
Uh, I would have said,
"Sister in blue, yes.
Sister in yellow, no."
But you're both going through to Hollywood.
Welcome to Hollywood!
# One and two! #
We're going to Hollywood!
Just around the corner from the sisters,
Jarrod Norell is warming up for his big moment.
Hey, hey, hey!
Want to see those judges, gotta have the energy.
Gotta have the enthusiasm.
Gotta have the passion.
Gotta show it from front to back.
Get that breath going.
Make sure that that's there.
Zzzzzzzz.
Gets your buzz on.
Rrrrr-rrrr-rroom!
Get your car started.
And not give in.
Not give in.
Hello.
How are y'all doing?
Hi, Jarrod.
Hi.
So you're a great singer.
I... I believe so.
Yeah?
One of the best?
Could be.
Really?
And you think you could win?
I really do.
All right.
What are you gonna sing?
Amazing Grace.
Amazing Grace
Gotta give it up to God.
All right.
# amazing grace #
# how sweet the sound #
# that saved a wretch #
# like me #
# I once was lost #
# but now I'm found #
# was blind #
# but now I see #
Thank you.
Oh, Good Lord.
What was that?
Do you really think you're a good singer?
Seriously?
I'm not trying to be rude.
Do you think you're a great singer?
Are you serious?
Honey, it sounded like a lawnmower.
I mean, it's just not...
Are you... are you seriously in agreement, man?
I'm sorry, honey.
Just... I don't... music is not... is not where you're headed.
All right, thanks a lot, Jarrod.
Yeah.
Guys, can I please have two seconds more, Man?
I'm just right here.
I'm tripping. I'm tripping right now.
Are you feeling me?
I'm tripping. I'm losing it.
I'm just trying my best.
Can I sing one more song?
Oh, Dog, Dog, the vocals.
Man, you can't sing, Dude.
# amazing grace #
No, no, no.
# how sweet #
# the sound #
No, no.
# that saved #
# a wretch like me #
Help.
Security.
# I once was lost #
It's a no.
# but now I'm found #
You're hearing me, Bud.
You're hearing me.
It's a no, it's a no.
You're hearing me, Man.
This way, let's go.
I can't... I can't leave.
I cannot leave.
I'm not try... I'm not going to get violent.
I'm not getting violent.
I'm asking you to leave.
Come on, Dog.
Are you kidding me?
Jarrod was obviously
agitated, and refusing to quit,
left security with no choice but to intervene.
Come on, Man, do you see me fighting for this show,
and now you're gonna kick me out like that?
Look, Dude.
Everybody get excited.
Go ahead.
Okay, you're gonna bend your knees
and you're gonna roll over and step up.
Come on, bend your knees.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Bend your knees and get up.
So...
if that's the way it's got to be, you guys take me out in cuffs.
You gotta take me out in cuffs.
Act like I can't sing, Randy.
Yes or no?
It's a no.
No, it's a no.
Come on, Man.
No.
Come on, man.
Coming up, a mistake ten years ago robbed him of his youth.
I spent four birthdays behind bars.
But what lies in Matt Lawrence's future?
An emotional conclusion after the break.
It's 6:00 PM, and day two in Orlando is winding down.
What was once 10,000 hopefuls has been whittled to less than a handful.
Orlando had proven to be the city of hope, with each person
auditioning for their own particular reasons.
Some came to make life better for a loved one, others to beat the odds.
Some came to conquer an insecurity.
The last contestant of the day was there for redemption.
My name is Matt Lawrence.
I'm 25 years old.
I'm from Starke, Florida, and I manage my father's trucking company.
When I was in high school,
I was the guy that had everything going for me.
But I also had this desire for adventure.
One day I came home, and there was a note that basically
said he was going on an adventure,
And one thing led to another.
I got into some trouble.
I robbed a bank with a BB gun when I was 15.
I spent four birthdays behind bars.
Being locked up was the hardest thing
that i've ever been through because...
it hurt my family so much.
I never saw my dad cry before that time.
Good luck in there, Matt.
Thank you, Man.
I auditioned for American Idol
because I want to do something
that'll make my family proud.
You know, I want to be able to,
you know, put a smile on their
face ten times more than I ever made them cry.
So... yeah.
How are you doing?
What's going on, Matt?
Not too much.
How are you guys?
Welcome, Man.
Thank you.
So is singing your dream?
It is.
Um, that's really all it's been up to this point.
I never really pursued it that much but, uh,
I got some positive feedback and figured
I'd give it a shot and see what happens.
All right, so what you singing today, Dog?
I'm singing Trouble by Ray Lamontagne.
Oh, get down.
Good to go?
Go for it.
# trouble #
# trouble, trouble, trouble #
# trouble been doggin' my soul #
# since the day I was born #
# worry #
#orry, worry, worry, worry #
# worry just cannot seem #
# to leave my mind alone #
# i've been saved #
# by a woman #
# she won't let me go #
# no, she won't let me go #
- All right. - Thank you.
- Brilliant. - Mm-hmm.
Brilliant.
You can really, really sing.
It almost feels like you could have written that song.
Oh, yeah.
That's how believable it was.
I don'mean that in a bad way.
It's just that it... it...
Well, maybe I did.
- No, no, but no, it... it felt authentic. - Yeah.
- I was very impressed. - Mm-hmm.
Well, thank you.
Very, very impressed.
Good for you.
I completely agree with Simon.
And what I love about you is,
you hit those high notes and I didn't feel like I was gonna fly through the window.
You have such control over your voice, you know?
And that's a hard song to sing.
You're so genuine, Dude.
That's what it's about, Man.
And you've got vocals.
What?
He's the real deal.
Let's take a vote.
Sime?
Easiest yes I've said today.
Kara?
I think one of the best.
Definitely one of the best today.
Welcome to Hollywood, Matt!
Whoo!
You made it, Dude.
Thank you, guys, so much.
He's gonna go top 12.
This represents an opportunity to change everything.
This represents an opportunity to
maybe get back some of the things I lost a long time ago.
My name is Matt Lawrence, and I'm the next American Idol.
And that's a wrap.
And that's where our story ends, for tonight at least.
In total, 31 contestants made their dreams come true in Orlando.
- Whoo! - Yes!
For them, this truly was the happiest place in the world.
See you in Hollywood.
Whoo!
Next week, idol is back home in Los Angeles, California.
Welcome to LA!
Where more unbelievable talent takes home the gold.
# get up and go #
# if I knew #
Dude, that was excellent.
Our guest judges get naughty.
I feel dirty.
Katy, you make me feel dirty.
And others get nice.
Are you sure this isn't my daughter?
But not everything's hot under the California sun.
It's not good. You shouldn't be doing this.
And Simon meets his biggest competition yet.
Simon Cowell, I'm going to Hollywood.
No, you're not.
Is idols in the city of Angels we are seeing are as angelic as they sing?
You want to leave on your own, or with an escort?