Tonight it's the final road show before Hollywood week.
Four yeses.
Dude, you're through to Hollywood!
And we are saving the best for last.
Lee, through to the next round.
Welcome to Hollywood, Lee!
More incredible moments and unbelievable voices.
I like you.
Yeah, you're cute.
Get ready for more outstanding new talent.
One of the best 16-year-olds I've ever heard.
You're definitely one of my favorites.
Mm-hmm.
As our biggest audition tour come to a climax.
The longest of journeys starts with the smallest of steps.
This year into the most famous arena in the history of television
have walked some of the most talented people we have ever seen.
And what does everyone remember?
# pants on the ground #
# lookin' like a fool #
# with your pants #
# on the ground #
# with the gold in your mouth #
"General" Larry Platt singing "Pants On The Ground".
# call yourself a cool cat #
# lookin' like a fool #
# walking downtown #
# with your pants #
# on the ground #
# get it up #
We knew it was gonna be popular...
You know, I have a horrible feeling that song could be a hit.
Yeah.
But even we were surprised at just how influential it turned out to be.
# pants on the ground #
# lookin' like a fool with #
# your pants on the ground #
It's in your homes.
# pants on the ground #
It's in our colleges.
It's even entered the political debate.
# pants on the ground #
# looking like a fool with #
# the pants on the ground #
Thank you, Mr. Speaker.
It's not exactly "Bohemian Rhapsody", but it is a number that stays with you.
And on this year's road, the contestants found
that picking that one special song was as crucial as ever.
Nobody should sing that song.
I didn't even know what song that was, man.
I think of all the songs in the world you could have sung,
that wouldn't have been in my top million.
Wow.
Returning Denver contestant Jessica Furney had
an interesting take with her song choice.
Back in season eight, she went with a "Joplin Track".
# honey, I know that she #
# told you she loved you #
# much more than I #
But one year and one makeover later...
Thank you very much.
She thought she'd stand out by singing a song co-written by you know who.
What are you gonna sing?
Um, I'm gonna sing "Footprints In The Sand".
Oh, that's a Simon co-write.
It is.
Wow.
I'm not doing it just to suck up.
I promise.
You wrote this song?
Co-wrote.
You co-wrote it.
Wow.
Jack of all trades.
- Anyway, it's a beautiful song, so good luck.
It's one of the greatest songs ever written.
Yeah, yeah.
# I promise you #
# I'm always there #
# when your heart is filled #
# with sorrow and despair #
# I will carry you #
# when you need a friend #
# you'll find my footprints #
# in the sand #
Beautiful song.
Nice song.
Wow.
Have you written any more songs?
No.
Why?
You're embarrassing me.
I had no idea he was a songwriter.
Yes, uh, can we get back to our contestant here?
What are we doing?
We got to vote.
Randy?
I'm gonna say yes.
I think you definitely improved.
Thank you.
Kara?
I'm gonna say yes.
And I'm gonna say yes too.
You've got a full house, Jessica.
Wow, well done.
Thank you so much.
See you later, guys.
Bye, sweetheart.
Whoo-hoo.
Jessica's risk paid off.
But as you'll see, making it all the way down the road
to hollywood takes more than just guts.
It takes ambition.
Singing is what I love to do, man.
Please, listen to me.
Perseverance.
This is my seventh time.
And of course a great voice.
# somewhere #
# over the rainbow #
Stay with us for more
incredible unseen talent, as we save the best for last.
# oh, I told you so #
In this hour, we may just meet the next American Idol.
# there'll come a day #
# when you walk out #
# of my dreams #
# face to face #
Or maybe not.
The road to hollywood is paved with attention-seekers,
and understandably so.
With thousands of people to compete against,
it is vital to stand out from the crowd.
In Boston, Amanda Shechtman showed me how to grab attention.
Act out.
# I think I did it again #
# I made you believe #
# we're more than just friends #
Okay, now do Lil Wayne.
I do all kinds of, like, voices,
and I can talk with my mouth closed.
This is me talking with my mouth closed.
Part of my journey is hopefully finding that
really special thing that I can do.
I just want my true, true voice to shine through,
And I'm pretty confident it will.
# wish I'd forget you #
# but you are here to stay #
# seems I met you #
# when my love went away #
# now every day I start by #
# saying to you #
# good morning heartache #
# what's new #
Okay.
Good.
Hmm.
I think you need to work on your expression.
Definitely.
Yeah.
I think it's the connection, really.
It's sort of about you figuring out who you are
and connecting to what you're singing.
Simon, what do you think with her connecting?
You didn't connect with me,
Amanda, to be honest with you.
Seriously?
Yeah. Yeah.
It's... it's hard for me to do the thing where I sing and I, like,
interact, because I've done so much theater, and I do this.
like, out here thing...
Yeah, that's it.
And I'm trying... like, I... I
really, like, I promise I can get into it.
Like, I really can.
I want to connect with people.
But you're such an actress.
Oh.
But you are, Amanda.
You're so dramatic.
Don't be sad.
You... you do have a good voice.
Oh, man, I can't believe this.
We're not trying to make you feel bad.
We're trying to help you.
I know. I understand.
Victoria, yes or no?
You know, I'm gonna... I'm gonna say yes.
I like you.
I do.
Kara, yes or no.
I'm gonna say yes.
Guys...
Simon, yes or no?
I promise... Okay.
Simon, stop it.
I'm...
Stop it.
That's... you know, what I think?
she really...
Singing is what I love to do, man.
Please listen to me.
It's good to be dramatic.
Yes.
I'm dramatic.
We're all dramatic.
Yes.
Randy's dramatic.
I have to say...
Oh, Simon, you're being mean.
Yes or no?
I know it's hard.
It pains you.
Yes.
You got four yeses.
Welcome to Hollywood!
Yes.
You made it.
You did.
Whatever you did, keep doing it.
I can't take anymore.
Oh, you can't take anymore?
You are dramatic.
Where's the curtain?
Are they still there?
Take your bow.
Yes.
Yes, thank you.
Lovely.
See you in Hollywood, doll.
Fabulous, fab... Encore, encore.
No more.
I love you.
Amanda with lots of drama.
So Amanda Shechtman is
awarded gold for her
performance.
And what award would be complete without an acceptance speech?
I can't believe this is happening.
This is my dream.
I really didn't think I was gonna get through.
I really didn't think I was.
I just want to be able to let my voice shine through, and be myself, and...
And I think...
This is just a dream come true for me.
Dramatic actress Amanda wasn't the only one
who showed they could do more than just sing.
Contestants bend over backwards to demonstrate their talent.
And we were never short of musicians.
Although instruments couldn't be played in the room,
They're often brought along.
Why did you wear a guitar for...?
It's kind of a comfort blanket for me.
But at this stage of the auditions,
these musicians must rely solely on their vocals.
# ain't no sunshine #
# when she's gone #
# hmm, hmm, hmm #
# ain't no sun #
# when she goes away #
# hmm, hmm, hmm #
# ain't no sunshine #
# when she's gone #
# and she's always #
# gone too long #
# anytime she goes away #
# take it #
# another little piece #
# of my heart now baby #
# yeah #
# break another little piece #
# of my heart #
# my heart now oh #
You're going to Hollywood.
Welcome to Hollywood.
Thank you.
100%.
Lee, through to the next round.
Welcome to Hollywood, Lee.
The golden tickets for Lee and Chrystal mean
They can finally play their instruments in Hollywood.
But these pieces of paper are not just the gateway to a golden future.
I'm going to Hollywood!
They're a prop.
Let's take a vote, Sime.
Yes or no?
So how would a ticket to Hollywood or success on this show impact you guys?
Oh...
It would mean the world to us.
The world, yeah.
He wants it.
His papa would be so proud.
Where there's wind, there is a contestant.
Ah, so sorry, man.
Aah!
# I got you #
# uh-huh #
Ah, the fake-out...
A time-honored tradition on idol.
If it was good enough for Daughtry,
It was good enough for this season's contestants.
# don't turn it loose now #
# hold it #
# a little bit longer now #
Whoo!
Even I got in on the act.
But as ever, Cowell had to have the last laugh.
He didn't make it.
Uh, sorry.
This always happens.
He has a tantrum about this far into the shooting,
And so he's got to go out and get a little bit of botox.
Does that mean he didn't make it?
Yes, idol just wouldn't be idol without the fake-out,
and the show wouldn't be the same without people like this.
You lost weight, you know that?
Ah, thank you, yes.
I've seen you on TV.
Coming up, the road to
Hollywood takes a few detours.
There's, like, a small schoolboy inside you.
But like so many of our contestants...
This is my seventh time.
We persevere and head back in the right direction with dazzling new talent.
Definitely one of my favorites.
The journey to Hollywood continues...
May I be excused?
After the break.
Welcome back to American Idol.
Whoo!
Yeah, man!
Welcome back to American Idol.
When you've done a show like this for nine seasons,
you're going to see some familiar faces.
I auditioned last year.
I auditioned for American Idol last season.
This is my fifth time auditioning.
Last season I did try out.
Let's not talk about that.
I cried,
a lot.
This year I feel much more comfortable in my own skin.
I think I could get farther this time.
I feel it. I feel it.
I feel it.
But remembering them is easier for some...
Welcome to Idol season nine.
She was here last year.
than others.
I don't remember any of these people.
Do you remember me?
Oh, I know this girl.
Hey.
You remember me.
This is the reunion show.
Simon, do you remember me?
No.
Rose.
You even said in my audition,
"You're one of the few I'm going to remember."
I tried out last year.
You thought we'd remember you, so you came in disguise.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Uh, it says here you're pretty sure I will remember you.
Mm-hmm.
I don't.
You don't?
Tan girl? Dark skin?
Really bronze?
Oh, no, you know what?
Yeah, it's beginning to ring a bell.
Um, you need me to explain anything?
Hey, what's up, people?
Yes, the tan.
Okay, um, my name is Chrystal.
Um, I just turned...
No, I want to hear about your suntan.
Okay, um, I'm singing and I'm telling you by Jennifer...
No, no, no, I want to hear about your suntan.
Oh, my suntan?
Yeah.
I go tanning.
No.
In Orlando, Lacey Brown hoped she had made a lasting impression in season eight.
Hello.
Hi.
Have we seen her before?
Yes.
Last year I was top 50 for season eight.
Lacey, how are you?
Good. How are you doing?
Good. How are you feeling?
I was sitting in the chair
next to Megan Joy, and I thought it might be that
they may put me and her both through.
Lacey...
- it's the end of the road. - It was disappointing at the moment,
but something inside of me said "This isn't the end of the road for you."
Immediately I knew.
People are gonna tell me no all the time.
You can't just take noes and live by 'em.
You got to turn 'em into yeses.
# somewhere over the rainbow #
# blue birds fly #
# well if blue birds #
# fly over the rainbow #
# then why #
# tell me why can't I #
# someday I'll wish #
# upon a star #
# and wake up where the clouds #
# are far behind me #
Thank you.
Okay, Randy, yes or no?
Uh, I actually like the tone of your voice.
I'm gonna say yes.
Kristin?
I loved it. Yes.
Kara?
You're definitely one of my favorites this season.
Yes.
You're through.
Welcome to Hollywood.
Yes.
Thank you so much.
Welcome to Holly... Welcome back to Hollywood.
She's so pretty.
So Lacey got a second shot at Hollywood.
Yeah!
Whoo!
In Denver, we meet a girl preparing for her seventh attempt...
Stephanie Fischer.
Seven's my lucky number.
I was born in the seventh month.
I was seven pounds and seven ounces.
I live at 7...
Well, I don't want to say my address, do I?
Seventh house on a street.
And this audition was particularly exciting to her.
I am so excited for Victoria Beckham.
She's my idol.
She's the most beautiful creature I've ever seen.
She's so pretty.
It's bad enough to have Simon,
who I have a huge crush on.
But Victoria Beckham?
Oh, my gosh.
Hi. Wow.
Wow.
You are...
I almost wore the same thing.
Yeah.
Okay, let's hear it.
# never know how much #
# I love you #
# never know how much I care #
# when you put your arms #
# around me #
# you give me fever #
# that's so hard to bear #
# uh, uh #
# when you kiss me #
# fever when you hold me tight #
# oh fever #
# In the morning #
# fever all through the night #
Thank you, Stephanie.
What did you think?
Terrible.
Honestly, you can't sing, sweetheart.
To be honest, I'm really starstruck by Victoria Beckham.
She's, like, my fashion icon.
Oh, thank you.
And, honestly, I wanted to cry when I came in here.
Thank you.
Would you like Victoria to turn away?
Do you want me to look the other way?
Yeah, you're putting her off.
Am I putting you off?
Okay.
Okay, she won't look.
Yeah.
# ooh #
# baby love #
# my baby love #
All right, turn around.
I think It was better when she was looking at you.
Yeah, yeah, better turned around.
That was even worse.
She was giving you good vibes, I think.
With the greatest respect,
you have a horrible voice.
Really?
Yeah, honestly.
Yeah, Stephanie, you are not got it going on on the vocals.
You can't give me, like, a few minutes to get un-nervous?
We'd need years, Stephanie.
We'd be in, like, American Idol 27.
Yeah.
Victoria, talk to Stephanie.
Come here.
Do you like what she's wearing?
No, you know, I think she has a very definite look.
I wouldn't say it's necessarily a look that I would go for.
I think you'd look good in that, V.
No, I wouldn't.
Come here.
Got to work on the vocs, baby.
Aw.
Come on.
You're gonna be fine.
You're a smart girl.
We've got to do the yessing and the noesing.
Yeah, yeah, will you step back over here?
No.
No?
Well, at least she's leaving with some dignity.
Did you just say no, Stephanie?
She did. Good.
I like your attitude.
Okay, It's a no.
Stephanie, what if it was gonna be a yes?
See, you don't even know.
Was it gonna be a yes?
No.
Well, there you go.
So for posh's number one fan, the seventh time was not a charm.
Maybe next year.
Luckily for us, each season we get a new batch of contestants,
as thousands of American kids hit sweet 16.
And this year's crop of 16-year-olds provided some of the best new talent yet.
# how can you walk #
# that extra mile #
# I see forgiveness #
# In your smile #
# So sure you'd reject me #
# Wrong again #
Thank you, Rachel.
# How am I supposed to live #
# Without you my love #
Whoo!
# how am I #
# supposed to carry on #
Thank you.
Oh, wow.
# I told you so #
# oh I told you so #
You definitely got chops.
I mean, there's no denying you can sing.
One of the best 16-year-olds I've ever heard.
I'm impressed.
You guys...
I'm going to Hollywood.
Hollywood!
Up next, you would believe what we save for you.
Definitely have a good voice.
As we meet more of the faces you'll see next week in Hollywood.
Four yeses.
Dude, you're through to Hollyweird.
But not everyone strikes gold.
Baby, you can't sing.
It's just not... Aw, no.
Stay with us as the talent flexes some muscle, while showing its softer side.
# I am this beautiful #
# man-flower #
# I will keep blossoming #
# and blossoming #
# I shine my beauty... #
You're joining us on the road to Hollywood.
This year, American Idol visited seven cities and saw over 100,000 contestants.
These idol hopefuls have come to us from all walks of life.
I'm a waiter.
I'm a photographer.
I'm a police officer.
And I'm a clown.
But right now, it's not the nine-to-five professional
that we want to talk about.
Athletes make up a large percentage of the contestants
that try out for the show.
And we want to pay tribute.
I'm a gymnast.
I play a little bit of ultimate frisbee.
I play college football.
I'm technically the female version of Bruce Lee.
For these contestants, it's a different kind of game.
But the idol auditions are a competition all the same.
Winning is the number one goal.
Put me in the game, coach.
And these athletes, just like other contestants,
soon find out that making it past the judges
can be a very tall order.
- What's your name? - Hi, I'm Adrian.
How old are you?
I'm 17 years old.
You're 17?
Wow.
How tall are you?
I'm 6'8".
Do you dunk?
I can't dunk.
I'm sorry. I'm a terrible jumper.
People think I should go into basketball, but swimming is my thing.
My coach calls me the Big Kahuna, the big fish.
I have a lot of nicknames.
It always has something to do with something big.
Big man, big kahuna,
Blonde-Zilla.
I love that name.
# I say love #
# it is a flower #
I am a beautiful man-flower.
I will blossom the beautiful, big petals blossoming out...
keep blossoming until it shows its entire glory and beauty.
What do you hope to prove in this audition today?
I would like to prove that,
um, it doesn't matter what size you are when you sing.
I got to tell you, for America,
I am the only one.
Wow, you're tall.
How tall are you?
I am 6'8".
Nice.
And what are you gonna sing?
I'm going to sing, um, a hit by Elvis Presley,
"Can't Help Falling In Love With You".
"Can't Help Falling In Love With You"
Okay.
Beautiful song.
Good luck.
# wise men say #
# only fools rush in #
# but I an... am #
# falling in love #
# with you #
Thank you.
Adrian, there's, like, a small schoolboy trapped inside you.
Either that, or you've eaten one.
"Let me out"
You know, you're a nice guy,
look, you're not a horrible singer.
No.
I mean, it just doesn't match you.
Yeah.
Randy, yes or no?
No, Adrian.
Yo, Adrian, this is not for you, baby.
- Kara? - Adrian, you are a very sweet guy, so...
But I have to say no.
And I... I encourage you to find something else.
Yeah, man.
Okay, it's a no, but nice to meet you, Adrian.
Nice to meet you, man.
- Nice guy. - Sorry.
You have my number,
if you want to do re-callbacks, then call me.
Okay.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Adrian couldn't deliver a championship performance.
You have my number.
You can just call me or send me an email.
Let me know when there's a job opportunity for me.
Maybe the outcome would have been
more favorable if he'd done some training,
like his fellow Orlando contestant.
My name is Michael Lynch.
I'm 26 years old.
And I'm a personal trainer.
I do, like, a circuit training.
Uh, a lot of body-weight action.
Big Mike is the next american idol, because I got these guns, baby.
Big guns, and as it turned out, big news.
So I've got my first child on the way, and, uh,
we just found out on Monday it's gonna be a baby girl.
Although everybody thinks it's gonna be a boy,
so we're gonna find out.
Yo, yo.
- What it is? - Hey.
How are you doing?
- Whenever you're ready, Honey. - All right.
# oh #
# my love #
# my darling #
# I've hungered for #
# your touch #
# a long #
# lonely time #
# and time #
# goes by #
# so slowly #
# and time can do so much #
# are you still mine? #
Okay, Michael, thank you very much.
Thank you.
Randy?
Uh, you can definitely sing.
He's kind of like a singing teddy bear.
All right, so let's take a vote.
Sime, yes or no?
I'm gonna say yes.
Kara?
Yes.
KC?
You have my vote.
Welcome to Hollywood.
All right, Baby, yeah.
So our father to be muscled his way into Hollywood.
Nice, Brother.
Yeah.
Whoo.
Back in Los Angeles,
Didi Benami showed a different kind of strength when she battled her emotions.
I am auditioning today in memory of my best friend, Rebecca.
Almost four years ago, she passed away, and it was horrifying.
I felt like I had lost a part of me.
# love of mine #
Rebecca is absolutely the reason that I pursue music.
She believed in me.
You know, and when I didn't even know if I could believe in myself.
So... Yeah.
I miss her.
# then I'll follow you #
# into the dark #
My audition today is emotional already, but I'm...
I'm sure it's gonna be crazy once I get up there and do this,
because I am singing in honor of Rebecca.
What are you gonna sing today?
Uh, it's a last-minute decision, but I believe I'm gonna sing "Hey Jude".
That's a great song.
Mm.
# any time #
# you feel the pain #
# hey Jude refrain #
# don't carry the world #
# upon your shoulders #
# well you know #
# that it's a fool #
# who plays it cool #
# by making this world #
# a little colder #
# nah, nah, nah, nah, nah #
# nah, nah, nah #
# hey Jude #
# don't let me down #
# you have found her #
# now go and get her #
# remember so let her #
# into your heart #
# then you can start #
# to make it better #
Thank you.
You really want it bad.
I do.
You do, yeah.
It's okay, Sweetie.
Did good.
Aw.
I'm sorry.
No, I know.
I know it's rough.
It's rough.
It's...
I know.
My heart is, like, beating out of my chest right now,
but I'm really excited that I did that.
- You sang really well. - Really well.
You did good.
You did.
Take a deep breath.
She did good.
I actually thought it was really cool.
You got good range.
And sounded like you had your own kind of sound jumping out,
so I actually liked you.
Let's take a vote and let's see, okay?
Randy.
Uh, I'm gonna say yes.
I'll give you another shot.
I think you got a good voice.
Thank you.
Simon?
Uh, a very small yes, Didi.
Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
But it's a yes.
Avril?
I would absolutely say yes.
I think you have huge potential.
You're going to Hollywood.
Welcome to Hollywood, Didi.
Aw, she's sweet.
See you later, Didi.
So Didi will be joining us in Hollywood.
I did it with everything on my mind and all my emotions,
and I tried to put it all in the back and just dig in and do it,
'cause this was my one shot.
So I... I did.
Coming up, they've faced adversity...
We had no money.
My dad couldn't keep a job.
Things just weren't good.
I didn't know we were poor when I was little.
I thought a lot of kids didn't eat dinner.
But what happens when they face our judges?
That wasn't even the melody, Sweetie.
The Road to Hollywood continues after the break.
You're back on The Road to Hollywood.
We've seen how our contestants come in many different shapes and sizes,
and how they embody different aspects of star quality.
In some, the judges found heart.
It's okay, Sweetie.
In others, they saw determination.
Singing is what I love to do, Man.
Please listen to me.
I can't...
And in Aaron Kelly from Orlando, they saw resilience.
When I was a year old,
things just weren't really going that great with my biological parents.
We moved around so much.
Uh, never stayed in one place.
We had no money.
My dad couldn't keep a job.
Things just weren't good.
Social services, about ready to step in, take me and my brother away from them.
My aunt and uncle did not want that.
They didn't want us going to somebody we didn't know
and never getting to see any of my family or real family again.
So they adopted us.
I do call my aunt "Mom", because the one who raised you is your...
is your mom.
This is my mom, Kelly.
I'm grateful for everything that she's done for me.
She's given up a lot to make sure I am... how I am today,
and I've had all the things in life that every 16-year-old should have.
I've lived a happy life, and hopefully it's gonna be... get a lot better.
What you singing?
Uh, I'm gonna do "The Climb" by Miley Cyrus.
Great song.
Do it.
Okay.
# I can almost see it #
# that dream I'm dreaming but #
# there's a voice #
# inside my head saying #
# you'll never reach it #
# there's always gonna be #
# another mountain #
# I'm always gonna want #
# to make it move #
# always gonna be #
# an uphill battle #
Okay.
All right. Cool.
Sime, what do you think of Aaron here, Man?
Uh, Aaron, I thought that was a good choice of song for you.
I think the moms will like you.
Uh, I thought it was a pretty good audition, Aaron.
Dude, I think it was a great audition.
I love everything about you.
I love the fact that you're 16, you're shy,
and that voice comes out of somebody that shy,
which is cooler to me and more endearing.
I'm with Randy.
Uh, let's take a vote.
Sime, yes?
Yes.
Kara?
KC?
Oh, yeah.
Yes for me.
Four yeses.
Dude, Aaron, you're through to Hollyweird.
Thank you all so much.
He's so...
He's adorable.
Aaron is now one step closer to fulfilling his dream.
I might even be a role model someday to kids everywhere.
Whoo!
And while Aaron's dream is to inspire,
people ultimately come here with one goal.
I'm the next American Idol.
But they all have different ideas of what they'd do with their fame.
I want to inspire other singers.
This's gonna change my zip code, my address.
Make people feel good.
My phone number.
I just want people to know my name.
My car, my gas quality.
'cause right now...
For Kimberly Bishop, it was about more than herself.
I feel like I have what it takes to be the American Idol
and the next pop singer, 'cause I have a really good heart,
and I would be very into recycling and helping kids in Africa.
Hello.
Hi.
You lost weight.
You know that?
Aw, thank you, yes.
I've seen you on TV.
Thank you.
Okay, and what are you gonna sing?
Katy Perry "I Kissed A Girl".
All right, good luck.
# this was not #
# the way I planned #
# not my intention #
# I got so brave #
# with drink in hand #
# lost my discretion #
# it's not what I'm used to #
# just want to try you on #
Okay, Kimberly.
Ooh.
I love all the struggling with your arm and pulling your hair out.
Yeah.
A seductive girl.
Yeah, you are.
I think you're naughty.
Okay, Randy, yes or no?
Wasn't good enough.
Mm-hmm.
Kara?
No, Kimberly.
I would have said yes.
But it's a no.
May I be excused?
Or would you like me to sing another song?
No, you're excused now, Kimberly.
You're definitely excused.
Kimberly, Honey, the other way.
Other way.
Turn left.
Kimberly has a... no yellow ticket.
They said I was naughty.
She'd be fun on a date, wouldn't she?
That was so weird.
Maybe that means I'm really good.
Do you want anything? No.
Are you having a good time? No.
What was the "may I be excused"?
I quite liked that.
At least Kimberly showed Orlando had manners.
Over in Dallas, Shenee Harris
was certain that she had Texas-size talent.
My mom's here today with me, and I'm really thankful that she came,
and, um, I always appreciate her, and I love her dearly.
Don't put lips and she used to always put lipstick on my jaw.
When I went to class, it would be some big, red lips on my jaw.
When I was pregnant with her,
the lord gave me a vision.
And the vision was it was a little girl baby,
and she was on my heel, and she would always,
always be singing, and I always told her, you know,
after she got old enough, that she had the gift to sing.
Was this dream very near that little girl in front of judges?
Yes, it is.
It's a dream.
Come true today.
# I keep falling #
# in #
# in love #
# with you #
# sometimes I love ya #
# sometimes #
# you make me blue #
# loving you darling #
Mm.
# makes me so confused #
# I keep on falling#
Thank you.
# in and out #
# of love #
Do you know what?
I actually can't hear that song anymore.
I'm actually allergic to it now.
Honey, that wasn't even the melody, Sweetie.
She doesn't even know it's not the melody.
She's not... this is not a good singer.
Can I try something else please?
No, Baby, you can't sing.
It's just not... oh, no.
Should we just vote on this?
# she's out of my life #
And hopefully out of mine soon.
Okay, right, Shaddaii,
it's... it's... Shaddaii, Shaddaii, it's a no.
It's a no.
Kara?
Yes or no?
N... no.
No, I'm sorry.
Baby, you can't sing.
- Okay, Randy? - No, no.
Okay, thank you Shaddaii.
Okay.
Thank you, Sweetheart.
After the break, the story of Hope.
I didn't know we were poor when I was little.
I thought a lot of kids didn't eat dinner.
We're saving the best for last as the road comes to an end.
And we'll lift the curtain on the dreams and the drama of our most tense Hollywood week to date.
I hated everything about that.
- Welcome back to... - American idol!
As our audition tour nears an end,
I'd like to thank all the cities for the warm welcomes.
Welcome to LA!
Welcome to Atlanta!
Welcome to Chicago!
Welcome to Denver!
But no one did hospitality better than Dallas, Texas.
Welcome to Dallas!
This is the greatest day ever at work.
And it was in the Lone Star State where we met Texas native hope Johnson.
I have a lot of siblings.
I have six sisters and a brother.
I had to overcome a lot of poverty,
which a lot of people I'm sure deal with that, but I didn't...
I didn't know we were poor when I was little.
I thought a lot of kids didn't eat dinner.
My parents would say, "you're gonna eat at school."
I used to take food from my lunch tray, take it home with me,
cause whenever my brother, little brother would tell me he was hungry,
and he would cry, so I would give my brother my food or my lunch.
I felt like...
you know, there's always tomorrow, and things are always gonna be better.
Just make it through the night, you know?
I'm sorry.
There's a lot worse things than just going without.
There's a lot worse.
Music's my escape.
I can sing a song and you'll know exactly what I'm talking about.
I hope the judges see the positive side of me, you know?
When I walk up, I hope like, "oh, she's a star."
I hope they see that.
# I hope you never fear #
# those mountains #
# in the distance #
# and never settle #
# for the path #
# of least resistance #
# living might mean #
# taking chances #
# but they're worth taking #
# and loving might #
# be a mistake #
# but it's worth making #
# and when you get the choice #
# to sit it out or dance #
# I hope you dance #
Okay.
All right, cool.
Hope.
There's something very interesting about you and your tone and just... I like you.
You're... you're... I'm gonna remember you.
Thank you.
I like you too.
I think... I think that you're very sweet.
There's a certain sort of innocence, and I love that song,
Love that you picked that song.
And it's one of the best lyrics I think written in a long time.
I agree.
You know, what's cool is that you've got a beautiful tone to your voice.
The only thing you need to work on is completing the phrases.
Letting them...
# last out #
I've heard that.
# make sure you close #
I like you.
Thanks.
Yeah, I like you.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're cute.
Okay, Randy, yes or no?
Yes.
Joe?
Yeah.
Kara?
I'd say yes too.
Four yeses.
Whoo!
Yeah, right, right, right.
This is ridiculous!
Oh, my god!
It's ridiculous.
Welcome to Hollyweird.
Gonna be ridiculous in Hollywood, yes.
It already is.
Season nine is already pretty ridiculous.
It's already ridiculous.
Yeah.
I'm going to Hollywood.
That was the most overwhelming experience
I think I've ever experienced so far in my life.
I'm so amazed that it actually...
it's actually happening.
This is real.
Like... It's real.
America, I am going to Hollywood.
Whoo!
So Hope, along with a select group of talented singers are all that remain.
They've taken great leaps of faith to get here,
- and it's been a long journey for all of us. - Y'all.
This season, over 100,000 people showed up.
Holla!
# tiptoe #
But only 172 walked out with gold.
Just say something like,
"my favorite judge."
And for them, the journey has just begun.
Yeah!
Daddy's going to Hollywood.
Yay!
Yay! Whoo!
Next week, it's the event you've been waiting for,
as Ellen Degeneres takes her permanent place at the panel.
You frighten me.
You were stalking us.
You were like a leopard behind a cage.
But it's not all fun and games.
That was really strange for me.
But I'm not sure you know how to perform.
That was painful.
That was really, really... dull.
Together we'll embark one journey known as Hollywood week.
Hollywood!
They may be the most talented
we've ever seen.
Very, very nice.
You're really a great singer.
That was amazing.
But they have never broken down quite like this.
I have so much...
I don't want to get cut, because I've worked so hard.
Now after this process, we'll be down to 12 guys and 12 girls.
Who will survive...
Oh, my gosh.
Hollywood week?