Hey, quick pop quiz.
What city has Idol visited five times,
has given us Fantasia, Clay Aiken, and Jennifer Hudson,
and is the birthplace of yours truly?
Yep, that's me.
- Howell Michigan. - No
- Phoenix. - Not it.
- Frisco. - Dallas.
No and no.
- Frisco. - No.
- Tampa. - No.
- New York. - No!
- San Diego? - Not it!
Rio de Janeiro, Brazil?
Not even close.
I mean, come on!
Was it really that hard?
American Idol is back in the peach state.
# same old place #
Welcome back to Hot-lanta!
Whoo!
And every time we come here,
the crowds are bigger than ever.
# on my way back to Georgia #
The 10,000 on hand were ready to show us
the depth of the talent pool in the deep south.
Bring it on, Simon.
Simon and Kara arrived ready to go.
But Randy still needed a little me time.
I don't want to get out.
Poor baby. Good thing we had our guest judge Mary J. Blige on hand.
I'm really excited.
I think I'm gonna be an honest judge.
I'm not gonna be so rigid,
but you have to just tell the truth.
The Atlanta auditions just couldn't be without her.
She's been called the empress of soul,
And this music legend has the goods to back it up.
Having sold over 40 million albums,
and with nine Grammys to her name,
Mary J. Blige has helped to redefine R&B
and has taken her place as a pillar of the music industry.
So here in Atlanta,
the contestants will walk into this elevator,
then hit the 27th floor.
On their way up, once they reach the top,
exit the elevator,
and the judges will listen to their song.
It's gonna be a long ride down if they don't get a golden ticket.
The judges were set,
And their first contestant,
27-year-old Dewone Robinson was feeling confident.
His success was clearly meant to be.
Music is in my blood.
It runs through my veins.
My great uncle discovered Gladys Knight and the Pips.
His name is Clyde.
And other kinfolks of mine,
He was playing the drums for Motown.
His name is Bobby. Motown bobby.
Well, I first found my voice when I was young.
I came home, and I sung this song.
I just made up a song, and my brother and sister said,
"where you learn that at? In church?"
I said, "no, I just made it up."
It just come natural.
Like a diamond in the rough.
When I go upstairs,
I'm gonna sing from the bottom of my heart.
Right through there.
Take it on up.
And I'm gonna sing the best to my ability,
so that I can go to Hollywood.
Yo, yo. What's up, man?
How you doing? You chilling?
Yes, sir. How you doing?
What's your name, man?
My name is Dewone Robinson.
- So you ready? - Yes, I'm ready.
- What you gonna sing? - I'm gonna sing something that I originally came up with.
Mm-hmm.
All right, cool.
# lady, I know you #
Hold on.
What's this?
What song is that?
- It's his original song. - Oh, it's an original song.
Okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah, sorry.
There you go. Start again.
Start over, yeah.
# la... #
And it's called what?
What's it called?
What's the song called?
It's called "Lady, We're Not Together Anymore".
"Lady, We're Not Together Anymore".
"Lady We're Not Together Anymore"
Okay. Now she knows.
Now she knows.
# lady, I know you #
# baby, I know you #
# la-la-lady, I know you #
# it's over #
Oh, please god.
- What you all want me to sing? - Honey...
Usher or something? I won't sing... Usher?
Honey.
Dewone, did you write that as a duet?
No, not a duet, sir.
No, not a duet. I was... I was...
You were playing both parts.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir, I was playing both parts at the same...
Okay, I can honestly say,
Dewone, it's one of the worst original songs i've ever heard.
I know.
I couldn't really sing at all,
Because you said... you said,
"uh, you... you're not doing it right."
"You're not... What is this called?"
Oh, honey, it had nothing to do with him.
I was gonna tell you what it was called,
but you just jumping up on me like...
No, no, I wanted to know what it was called.
What y'all want me to sing? Rick James?
# fire and desire, baby #
Huh?
You got me shell-shocked.
He jumped on me.
I didn't jump on you, Dewone.
I asked you what the song was called.
He said "what is this called?" He said "what is this called?"
Okay, Dewone, I'll tell you what.
Experiment.
I'm not gonna ask you a single thing.
Sing the song again.
# lady, I know you #
# baby, I know... #
Okay, Dewone.
# hey, la... #
Dewone, that was even worse.
I can sing. But I was singing...
But I was trying to sing.
Dewone.
Dewone
What are you talking about?
# lady, I know you #
Oh, god, no. Please.
- Security! Security! - Bye!
What you all want me to sing?
- Security! - What you all want me to do?
- Leave. - Out, out, out.
Still have a nice, blessed day, and god bless you all.
God bless you.
# it's over #
# with me #
Uh, yes, it is, Dewone.
But Atlanta is just getting started.
Coming up, Georgia delivers some spectacular talent.
So far, best vocal we've seen yet.
- I love you. - I mean, it was just dope.
Whoo!
We're deep in the south.
Welcome to Vonore, Tennessee.
And the southern belles are a-ringing.
# well #
It's like a cat barking.
This is gonna take my dream away from me.
Plus drama like we've never seen before.
- What are you doing? - Lamar, Lamar.
- *** your mom. - Oh!
That... can't sing a lick.
And one audition you'll
definitely be talking about tomorrow.
I have a horrible feeling that song could be a hit.
Boom!
Atlanta gets down after the break.
I would really love to go to Hollywood.
Not based on that audition,
you won't be.
Welcome back to Atlanta!
We're hotter than ever!
Whoo!
We're back in the Atl.
They call it hot-lanta,
but the talent is leaving the judges cold.
I'm good at high notes, like,
# and she coming like ooh #
# ooh, baby #
# high, high, high #
# whoo #
Whoo! Whoo!
Whoo!
That's turned everything around.
Downstairs, the holding room is rallying
To get their first golden ticket.
# Straight line champions #
# Compete with class #
# you know and I know #
# We'll kick your (ass) #
On deck is our next contestant,
26-year-old Kia Johnson.
Maybe her bright and sunny smile
can warm up the judging room.
- Good afternoon. - Hello.
- Like your hair. - Thank you.
- How are you? - I'm ecstatic.
So you competed for a Miss America competition,
- and you won Miss Congeniality? - Yeah.
So you didn't get the "I'm good-looking".
You got the "I'm a good personality".
- Yeah. - Which is a great award.
I'd rather have the other one.
Well, of course you would. Of course you would.
You wouldn't get any award.
- Anyway. - Who would enter a beauty competition
and want to get "I've got a good personality"?
- Me. - I like this girl.
Oh, you a good girl. We like that.
And it's all about you.
- You're beautiful. - Thank you.
I appreciate that.
So I guess you want to hear me sing, maybe?
- Yeah. - Okay, um, I'm gonna do Titanic song.
# you're here #
# there's nothing I fear #
# and I know that my heart #
# does go on #
# and we'll, we'll stay #
# forever this way #
# you're safe in my heart #
# and my heart will go on #
# and on #
Thank you.
- What'd you think? - If you ask me...
- Mary, what'd you think? - If you asked me vocally,
truthful and honest, she can sing.
You definitely can sing.
I like the way you close some of the phrases.
Like, "oh. That's good, right there."
Yeah.
I think that I can really see how you won that contest,
cause your personality really comes across.
Genuine.
You're very genuine,
and you're nice to look at when you're performing.
You don't make any crazy faces,
- and you do have really good vocals. - Thank you.
I like... I like you, but, you know,
if I'm being honest with you,
I could imagine you standing in line,
and sort of getting the part in Oklahoma.
But you know what she did?
It was the way she ended certain things,
and she made that big song that everybody knew
and auditioned with her own.
- Yeah. - You had some good riffs.
- I like you, though. - Thank you, Simon.
- Yeah. - That means a lot.
Thank you. Okay, we're gonna vote.
- Randy? - Uh, yes, I love this girl's voice.
I think you can sing, man.
- Thank you, Randy. - Yes.
- Kara? - Definitely.
- Oh. - Yes.
Uh, and I'm gonna say yes as well.
Four yeses. Welcome to holly-weird.
Oh, my god! Thank you so much.
She's so cute.
She's sweet.
Got the golden ticket!
Oh, my god! Thank you, god!
Whoo! Going to Hollywood.
Super excited.
Now I can do a real dance move.
Kia has finally got Atlanta cooking.
And the judging room began to sizzle.
# there's always gonna be #
# another mountain #
# I'm always gonna want #
# to make it move #
# always gonna be #
# an uphill battle #
# sometimes you gonna have #
# to lose #
# don't make me close #
# one more door #
# I don't want to hurt #
# anymore #
# if you don't let me know #
# what you're feeling #
Mm-hmm.
# yeah, ooh #
Whoo.
# it's impossible #
Thank you.
I think that was the best we've seen all day.
I really do.
One billion percent yes.
You're going to Hollywood!
- Four yeses to Hollywood. - You deserve it.
- Whoo! - Welcome to Hollywood.
- It's a yes. - Thank you.
Welcome to Hollywood, Miriam.
Now we're talking.
Atlanta is taking care of business.
And our next contestant has spent his life
caring for another.
I'm Jermaine Sellers.
I'm 26 years old, and I'm from Joliet, Illinois,
And I'm a church singer.
Is that where you work? That's your job?
That's what I do for a living.
- You get paid to sing? - Yes.
- That's cool. - Yes.
This is what I've wanted my whole, entire life.
So my mom's like
"Jermaine, you should go and get an audition"
My mother has a condition
is called Spinal Bifida,
where she has grown spurs on her spinal cord,
and sometimes she's in a lot of pain,
she can't move at all.
I've been taking care of my mom since I was 17.
If I make it to Hollywood,
I'll be proving myself that I can sing.
This is my dream, and I'm gonna make it happen.
- How are you, Jermaine? - I'm doing good.
Well, you seem like a nice guy here.
Caring for your sick mom and singing at church.
- Yes. - That's really great.
I'm a church boy.
What are you gonna do here today?
Sing. I love to sing.
And what are you gonna sing? Huh?
- What did you do? - He's gonna juggle.
I'm singing Joan Osborne
What If God Was One of Us.
What If God Was One of Us
Oh, that is a great song.
Wow.
# yes, yes #
# god is good #
# and yes, yes #
# god is great #
# yes, yes #
# yeah, yeah, yeah #
# oh, what if god #
# was one of us #
# just a slob like one of us #
# he's just a stranger #
# on the bus #
# trying to make his way home #
- Wow. - Jermaine, I love you.
- Wow. - That was a great interpretation of that song.
It really was.
Like, and I like that you came in here,
and you picked something that really you felt.
Listen. This, so far, all the cities,
best vocal we've seen yet.
You've got skills.
- This kid is hot time. - He is.
This kid is... This is the real deal right here.
Thank you.
- That was incredible. - Thank you.
It was so much control.
It was anointed.
It was all of the above.
Let's take a vote. Randy?
Uh, ask Simon first.
Sime?
- Yes. - Thank you, Simon.
- Mary? - I say yes.
- Thank you. - Definitely.
- 100% yes. - Thank you.
Million, thousand, 110% yes.
Welcome to Hollywood, Jermaine!
- Thank you. - I got my ticket.
# I got my ticket #
# ticket, ticket #
Mom?
Oh, I made it.
Whoo, baby! Yeah!
I will call you back, ma.
Bye.
She's gonna call the whole neighborhood now.
While Jermaine heads to Hollywood
and his mother rings the neighbors,
We head to a break.
Can hot-lanta continue to heat things up?
- You were fearless. - That was beautiful to me.
That... was great.
Or is the atl just hot-headed?
Y'all.
Plus we meet a small-town girl with big dreams.
I want to make something of myself.
I am. I'm stoked about being here.
Welcome back.
And almost done with the first day of auditions,
and Atlanta has shown us once again
why we love this city.
I'm going to Hollywood, baby!
Yeah!
High hopes and even higher temperatures
have everyone ready to get to that 27th floor.
And as the Georgia crowd thinned,
a colorful personality began to emerge.
I'm Christy Marie, and I just turned 25.
What do you do for a living?
I am a TV show hostess and producer
for Georgia TV's 411 the show.
I always get people to do 411 the show,
cause it's so much fun.
411 the show.
411 the show
So, in other words, if I were to incorporate that,
it would be, "This is American Idol."
- Yes, exactly. - That's how we'd start the show?
If the key to success is to do you,
then this is doing me, Christy Marie.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
All right. You're 25 from Atlanta.
It says you're a TV show host.
- What do you host? - I am.
It's called 411 the show.
And it's all about the fiery 411
on what makes hot-lanta so darn hot.
Whoa. You're like a walking commercial.
I would love to sing for y'all Pat
- Benatar's Love Is A Battlefield. - Do it.
# oh, whoa, whoa, whoa #
# whoa #
# we are young #
# heartache to heartache #
# we stand #
# with no promises #
# no demands #
# love is a battlefield #
# we are strong #
# no one can tell us #
# we're wrong #
# searching our hearts #
# for so long #
# both of us knowing #
# love is a battlefield #
- Thank you. - It is, girl.
- Wow. - It is.
- Wow. Wow. - This is my battlefield today,
because this is my love.
Singing is my life.
Music is my passion.
I would really love to go to Hollywood.
Well, not based on that audition,
you won't be, Christy.
Uh, it was a terrible version of the song.
Honey, it's not gonna work out.
We got our own 411 for you.
This is not... shouldn't be your career, sweetie.
You seem like a really sweet girl, but...
- I think it's more of a 911. - Yeah, exactly.
Emergency.
It's a no, Christy, but nice to meet you.
- Sorry, Christy. - Thank you for coming out, babe.
What do you think's gonna happen when she comes down?
Ooh, I hope she's got that golden ticket.
I hear the elevator moving,
so we may have a verdict.
I go up there, I sing for them, I, you know,
I put on the show, I give it my heart and soul,
and they're just like, "no, no."
I thought they were just being ridiculous.
"we think your show should be called 911 instead of 411."
This is one show I won't be promoting.
Random strangers that I don't know are clapping for me,
Telling me I sound amazing.
Well, the good news is,
Christy has plenty to talk about on her show.
Back in the room,
quite a few others were getting
the 411 on their singing voices.
And it's a long elevator ride down from that 27th floor.
I'm sorry, no.
# I'm going down #
- I'm gonna say no. - Can I sing something else?
Chelsea, that's it.
God, I didn't go through.
It's not enough, sweetheart.
It's really not.
I wish I could say yes, but I can't.
Singing is not for you, sweetie.
I'm gonna say no, man.
I didn't think it was a great audition, man.
Uh, no.
# baby, my whole world's #
# upside down #
- You didn't make it? - No.
Well, if you don't like the elevator,
you can always take the stairs.
Or if you're the last person of the day
and you live in rural Tennessee,
you could just jump.
Hi, I'm Vanessa Wolf.
I jump bridges. Peace out.
Ow!
Welcome to Vonore, Tennessee.
There ain't really much to do in Vonore,
So I jump bridges.
I like jumping bridges.
I like... the higher the better.
Don't try this at home.
This is risky business.
100% pure beef.
Vonore, it's about the smallest town probably in Tennessee.
My mom lives right down the road.
I go see her every day.
Come here, Clem.
I don't really have a life.
Never goes to the movies.
Or the mall. Or anything.
I'm stuck in Vonore.
I can't get out.
# I was lost #
# in the lakes #
I don't really have very much, you know?
I got this dress.
I think I got a good deal on this.
Got this for $4.50 at the dollar store out in Smyrna.
I come out for American Idol
cause I feel so trapped.
I want to make something of myself.
This is her dream.
And if she works to achieve it,
I'm standing behind her 100,000%, you know?
I love you, mama.
You make me feel good about myself.
This is the biggest thing that's happened to me. I am so nervous.
I know the judges, they are high-profile people,
And I don't want them to, like, look down on me,
or nothing like that.
You know.
What's life without a risk or two?
You know? Today is... most important day of my life.
I am. I'm stoked about being here.
Hello.
- How are you? - I'm doing pretty good.
- Where you from? - I'm from Vonore, Tennessee.
- "Vonroe"? - Vonore.
- "Vonroe"? - Vonore
V-o-n-o-r-e.
V-o-n-o-r-e
What you gonna sing?
Uh, Wagon Wheel, by Old Crow Medicine Show.
Okay.
# well, I'm #
# headed down south #
# to the land of the pines #
# and I'm thumbing my way #
# into north caroline #
# staring up the road #
# and pray to god I see #
# headlights #
# well, I made down the coast #
# in 17 hours #
# picking me a bouquet #
# of dogwood flowers #
# and I'm a-hoping for raleigh #
# I can see my baby tonight #
# so rock me, mama #
# like a wagon wheel #
Okay, okay.
All right.
I love that song.
I can tell. Wow.
I'm really nervous.
Vanessa ready for this audition?
Yes. Yes, I believe she is.
- Nerve-racking? - Yes.
Instead of butterflies, I got frogs.
You got... instead of butterflies you have frogs?
Yes. Vessa, I know it's really nerve-racking
to get up here, but, you know, I got to say, uh,
you were a lot better than I thought you were gonna be.
- Really? - You're a country singer,
and that's what you should be doing,
Because you're really true to it.
When you're singing it,
it feels real authentic.
Well, I am from the country.
You're a country girl.
Right smack dab in the middle of it.
That's right.
Vanessa, I like you.
- Well, I like you. - There's something about you I like.
I like all y'all.
Um, I think that you are incredibly ill-prepared
for this...very, very nervous.
But when you are good, you're really good.
- Mm-hmm. And you're distinct. - Yeah.
Um, and it's all about self-belief with you, sweetheart.
But you stand out in the crowd for me, and I like you.
And I think you're very authentic.
If I didn't have a dress on,
- I'd throw you a backflip, Simon. - Ah...
Randy, yes or no?
I'm gonna say yes to the country girl from the country.
- Vanessa, yes. - Vonore, Tennessee.
- Vanessa Jo. - Kara?
- Vanessa Jo - Kara?
Very authentic, and I like that about you.
Keep singing country. Yes.
Yes to the country girl.
Uh, yes, to you, Vanessa.
Are you serious?
We are 100% serious.
Welcome to Hollywood, Vanessa!
Ow! Yeah!
Whoo! Whoo!
Yes.
My mom's gonna have a heart attack.
But, Vanessa, you've got to start practicing.
Mm-hmm.
You got to start believing in yourself.
Otherwise you're gonna get swallowed up in Hollywood, right?
- That's right. - None of my friends is gonna believe this.
- Take the ticket, you go. - Take your ticket. Show 'em all that ticket.
- Yay. - Thank you, guys.
See you later.
- I like her. - Oh, jeez.
I can't believe this is happenin' to me.
Yeah, I like her voice.
- She's authentic. - Sweet girl.
- She's Rike. - Wow, okay.
Whoo!
Ow! Whoo!
Man, I'm going to Hollywood.
I'm gonna ride on an aeroplane.
And eat peanuts on a aeroplane.
- Have you been on a plane before? - No.
- You've never been? - No.
Goodbye, Vonore, Tennessee!
Mom, I am going to Hollywood.
Whoo!
# seems so small #
With that, a very successful day one
in Atlanta comes to a close.
Coming up, day two brings incredible highs.
# and I #
Oh, god.
# I #
And unbelievable lows.
And who is Kara?
I ain't never heard of that.
As the amazing talent...
- Whoo-hoo! - I'm loving Atlanta.
Stays alive.
Have you ever died before?
All right, Mary. Mary's upset.
It's early in the morning here in Atlanta,
And our crew is finishing last-minute preparations
for the start of the second day of auditions.
Outside, enthusiastic crowds are lining up.
Remember this face.
Upstairs, our judges are getting settled in.
- Yeah. - Oh, let's do it.
And yesterday must have been a good day,
because today Simon is far less cranky than normal.
My name is Simon.
- Hi. - I'd like to sing.
You know, people come to this show to change their lives,
to turn their luck around.
I think this next contestant
could use a little bit of that.
I'm Jesse Hamilton.
I'm 26 years old, and I'm from Anniston, Alabama.
I've come close to death quite a few times.
Well, tell me about the close calls.
What do you mean?
I've almost died three times in the last...
My whole life, so...
- You almost died... How old are you? - 26.
- You almost died three times? - Yeah.
When I was real young, I had tick fever.
My grandpa came in and found me in my crib.
He said I was limp as a dishrag.
So I almost died, they said.
Well, I was out shooting pistols with my buddy,
and I almost got hit by a speeding bullet.
The third one, I almost got ran over in my yard,
uh, about two months ago.
Whoo!
Missed me about from there to you.
- Wow. - Yes.
It's just the good lord looking at me.
That's all it is.
Just blessed. He's got a reason for me.
That's the way I look at it.
You're excited to be here.
- Yeah. - You've been through a lot.
You're a survivor.
Are you a good singer?
We'll find out.
Oh, hey.
- Hey. - How are you?
I'm all right. How about you?
- Uh, what's your name, please? - Jesse Hamilton.
Jesse Hamilton. Um, have you ever died before?
I've came close, but, you know, I'm blessed.
Oh, I thought he was saying he looked like he had died.
Have you ever sang in public before?
- No, sir. - No.
Have your friends heard you sing?
- No. - Right.
No one's ever heard you sing apart from your mother?
- Just my mom. - Good, Jesse.
Okay. Uh, what's the song, please?
Can I try a Garth Brook's song?
That's what I want to try.
They said I'm good at that.
- I want to try that. - Go on.
Oh, man, I'm...
I done froze. I'm so sorry.
- It's just... - What...what was the name of it?
She's upset.
- It's okay, Mary. - What was the name of it?
Garth Brooks, um...
The river. That's it.
Oh, it was the river. The river.
Garth Brooks.
- Okay. - Okay, Mary, it's okay.
If I can get the first line going, I...
It'll be okay. All right, Mary. Mary's upset.
- Mary, honey. - Mary's having a hard time.
You better do it quick, because Mary's really...
Mary's having a hard time.
Mary's feeling your pain and
your loss and everything.
Oh, god.
I'm so sorry, I can't...
Go for it, man.
The river.
Go ahead.
# sailin' on the river... #
And, um...
Sorry. We're okay, now.
- I'm just... - Sail down the river.
I'll try.
If I had the first sentence...
I got a mental block all of a sudden.
I could go with...
Does anyone know the song?
Uh, I know Garth Brooks
If tomorrow never comes.
"If tomorrow never comes"
Very sad, though.
# if tomorrow never comes #
Yeah.
# will you know how much #
# I loved her #
# did I try in every way #
# to show her every day #
# that she's my only one #
# and if my time on earth #
# were through #
# and she must face this world #
# without me #
Okey, what was that?
It was Garth Brook's, man.
If tomorrow never comes.
I didn't recognize that.
Um, Jesse, I mean, look.
The whole thing was terrible.
Uh, you're a nice guy,
but this is absolutely not for you.
And you're a welder, right?
Yes, that's right.
There's nothing wrong with that.
Go back to weld.
- Are you good in welding? - It's dangerous.
It's dangerous in here too, honey.
Well, if anyone's gonna survive welding, it's you.
It's fine, you know...
Did you just say, "if anybody's gonna survive..."
Well, because this guy's got nine lives.
Oh, my god.
That's a great profession for you.
It's true.
Okay, yeah, Jesse, full house, four noes,
But thank you very much.
- All right, thank you. - Sorry, Jesse.
That way.
# sometimes late at night #
- Whoa, look out. - I'm all right.
# and watch her sleeping #
He's coming down.
# she's lost in peaceful #
# dreams #
# so I turn out the light #
Didn't make it.
- Didn't make it? - No, they tore me up, man.
They crucified me, man.
Right there.
Take care, guys. Appreciate it.
We'll see you later, yeah?
Though his idol journey may be over,
this definitely won't be the end of Jesse.
With his chin held high,
he'll hopefully move on to greener and safer pastures.
And by mid-morning, misfortune seemed to plague everyone
that stepped foot into the judging room.
Honey, I'm sorry.
It's not good news.
I want this so badly.
No, dude, you're not ready yet.
You need more experience.
They're gonna take my dream away from me.
# if tomorrow never comes #
I think that could get quite annoying,
actually, if I'm being honest.
Simon is...
He said I was whiny.
# if tomorrow never comes #
I'll get my guitar and I guess I'll just be singing the blues on the way home.
Coming up...
# and I #
Oh, god.
Can Atlanta turn its luck around?
Hi.
Maybe.
Y'all!
Or maybe not.
It's gonna take an arresting performance to save the day.
The senior police officer is hot.
We are back in the great state of Georgia.
A couple of seasons ago,
we introduced instruments to the idol stage,
And since then it's made for
some pretty spectacular performances.
However, in that first audition in front of the judges,
You can't play an instrument.
I think our next contestant may have found a loophole.
My name's Holly Hardin, I'm 20 years old,
And I'm from Rockmart,Georgia.
And I'm a human guitar.
My friend's like, "you look cute!"
And everybody was like,
"Holy... Let me tune your guitar."
They were like, "let me strum you."
What's bigger, your glasses or your voice?
Probably my voice.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
I think when I go in there to see the judges,
I'm gonna do really good.
This might be a little bit distracting for the judges.
Are you worried about that at all,
that this might be a distraction, that it might...
No, I think it's kinda cute. I'm the next...great thing.
Guitar girl.
Holly, head on up there. 27.
All right. That's the number.
# we're gonna rock #
# this town #
# rock it inside out #
Whoo!
- Wow. - Hi.
- Hello, Holly. - Hi.
Why have you walked in as a guitar?
Well, because, like, I was a guitar for Halloween,
And everybody was like, "that's so cute."
So I figured, since I sing,
I was gonna be a guitar.
- Right, okay. - I got my glasses too.
You want to see these?
Oh, yeah, let's get the whole visual.
Yep, that just completes everything, Holly.
That's it.
Do you think you can win this show?
I do, I do think I can be the next American Idol.
All right, Holly, and what's the song?
Um, You ain't woman enough to take my man, by Loretta Lynn.
Wow.
All right, we're all yours,
Holly.
Holly
# you come to tell me #
# somethin' #
# you say I ought to know #
# he don't love me anymore #
# and i'll have to let him go #
# say you're gonna take him #
# oh, but I don't think #
# you can #
# 'cause you ain't woman #
# enough #
# to take my man #
Do you understand how this...
You can keep them on. Okay.
- How... - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Slightly bizarre this is that you're dressed as a guitar,
but also look a little bit like an insect
singing country and western?
I think it's cute.
Well, I know it's cute.
It just wasn't quite what we were looking for,
I don't think, Holly, when we set out this year.
But you're fun.
You've got great personality.
And I can always lose the guitar outfit.
- Really? - Yeah!
Okay.
Of course!
Randy, what do you think?
You're funny, Man.
You're hilarious.
You are.
Kara, what do you think?
You know, Holly, normally,
If someone dressed up in a guitar like that,
I just would write them off.
But I kind of...
She's a ballsy girl to come in like that in that getup.
And, you know, you got a good voice.
Thank you.
You do, you're like a country girl.
What do you think, Mary?
I don't get it.
Not many people do.
- Well, we're gonna vote. - OK
Randy.
Randy
Since I love the guitar, I'm gonna say yes.
- Kara. - The whole thing's crazy,
but I did hear some singing talent in there.
I feel like I got to give you another shot.
- Yes. - Mary.
I would say no.
Come on, Simon.
You're gorgeous.
Oh, come on.
He is.
Do you honestly think that I'm the sort of person
that would respond to that kind of flattery?
Aah!
I got it!
We've got our first person
from day two heading to Hollywood.
Whoo! Going to Hollywood!
Going to Hollywood!
But unlike Holly and her guitar,
right now the judging room needs some tuning.
# nothing's real #
# I just dream about you, baby #
It's like a cat barking.
- Huh? - Yeah, pretty much.
It shouldn't happen.
# when will my reflection #
# show who I am #
# insi-i-ide #
Terrible. No, no.
Singing's not your thing.
Don't... don't even...
Don't gas yourself up like this.
Britney Spears changed your life?
What if it's not good news?
- What are you gonna do? - What's that mean?
It is what it is.
All right, good. Good luck.
# oops, you #
# think that I'm standing #
# from above #
# I'm not that innocent #
Oops is right.
Well, Britney Spears may not have changed
the next contestant's life,
but she's hoping to get a trip to Hollywood that will.
- Hello, Mallory. - Hello.
Uh, so you're Mallory Haley.
You're 20. From where?
Winner, South Dakota.
Wow, okay.
All right, so what are you gonna sing today?
I'm going to sing Piece Of My Heart.
Go for it.
# each time I tell myself #
# I think i've had enough #
# well, I'm gonna #
# show you, baby #
# that a woman can be tough #
# so come on, come on #
# come on and take it #
# take another little piece #
# of my heart now, baby #
# of my heart, I know you will #
# and break it #
# break another little piece #
# of my heart now, baby #
# 'cause you know you got it #
# if it makes you feel good #
# so good #
All right, cool.
Uh, Mary, what do you think of Mallory?
She... wow.
I hope I'm not premature.
She could go to Hollywood.
Like some... that was great.
That was the best vocal I heard.
Thank you.
Like, I mean, it was just dope.
That was beautiful to me.
- I liked it. - Thank you.
I really like her too.
I mean, I think what's great about you
is you came in here, you know who you are,
you know what you want to do.
I think you got a good look too.
I think you're a really beautiful girl.
I like you being a country singer,
and I like that you claimed and owned that.
You got a good voice.
What I was really impressed about was that.
The fact was is that you were fearless
during that audition, and it didn't...
Didn't let it show.
You had great fun, great energy.
Emm... and I like you.
Randy, yes or no?
Yes.
- Mary? - That was great. I say yea
- Kara. - So yea, yea, 100%.
- Amazing. - You got four yeses.
Welcome to Hollywood! Go!
Beautiful girl, right?
- She's great. - She's good.
Yep, it was effortless and she was confident.
Bam!
So Mallory nabs a golden ticket.
And there were plenty more to go around in Atlanta.
Yay!
I'm loving Atlanta.
Atlanta is fire right now.
I'm going to Hollywood, Baby!
Yeah!
After the break, can Georgia keep this winning streak alive?
# and with a broken wing #
They're gonna have to stick
together to make it through.
What happens if somebody
makes it and somebody doesn't?
That's not gonna happen.
This is gonna be really
awkward for the two of you now.
The best friend I could ask for.
Welcome to Atlanta.
Ah.
It's a little past noon here in Atlanta,
and you know what that means.
It's time for some Skiiboski.
Skiiboski.
Skiiboski
Skiiboski is the thing.
Skiiboski, Baby.
My name Antonio Willa,
but people call me Skiiboski.
# skii-bo-ski #
And please say the Baby.
Skiiboski, Baby. Yeah.
When I dance, I ski, and when I blow,
I blow out miles when I sing my R&B.
So all you gotta do is just watch TV.
And you gonna see,
I'm gonna blow your mind indeed.
Yes, Skiiboski.
S-k-i-i-b-o-s-k-i.
There's only one "i" on that.
Okay, we got a misprint.
When I get in that judge room,
they gonna throw their hands up.
"Skiiboski, we been waiting on you."
I am the next American Idol.
Baby! Skiiboski.
Of course. Yes.
Skiiboski.
Skiiboski
Is that what that says on your shirt?
Skiiboski. Skiiboski.
Skiiboski Skiiboski
But it's spelled wrong.
Right?
Oh, well, you know,
that's what we got discounts for.
You know? Just keeping it real.
So you're the next big thing?
- Biggest thing. - You, for sure?
Phenomenal.
- We're gonna be blown away? - Blown away.
Yeah, he says it.
Mary's just gonna, like,
get out of her chair and scream.
All right, so wait a minute.
- What you gonna sing? - Grapevine.
Go for it.
# I bet you wonder #
# how I knew #
# 'bout your plans #
# to make me blue #
# with some other guy #
# that you knew before # that y#
# between the two of us guys #
# you know I love you more #
# oh, I heard it #
# through the grapevine #
Whoo.
# and I'm just about #
# to lose my mind #
# honey, honey, yeah #
Antonio.
Antonio
It's more... it's a package deal.
It's a package?
Really? What else?
Because I'm liking the dollar store.
What?
You know, with the dollar store,
even with the dollar store,
you can have everything you want in that one package.
And it don't cost you no more than a dollar.
- Dollar killer? - Okay, look... - I'm worth a lot.
That didn't even make sense,
- what you were just saying. - No.
Like the dollar store?
He just said he's worth a dollar.
Look, to be honest with you,
the outfit kind of put me off.
Um, the singing was awful.
The dancing was terrible.
- Oh, come on! - Oh.
What do you think, Kara?
I mean, I gotta tell you,
I thought when you walked in here, Skiiboski,
whatever is going on here,
that it was gonna be a disaster.
Really.
And you really had a good voice.
Well, once you feel me, I feel you.
You know what, I...
What else is there to feel now
since I felt you today?
I'm really impressed.
Vocally, Man, you have...
You have a great voice.
Um, image-wise, if you can make
that match what your vocal is doing,
you gonna be all right.
Well, I'm preppin'.
I'm gonna prep for you. Believe that.
Heh, thank you.
- Okay, now... - Listen, let me just say...
You got some good vocals,
but I would lose all the other nonsense.
Okay.
All right, let's take a vote here.
- Sime. - A resounding no.
Mary, yes or no?
I absolutely think he should go to Hollywood.
His voice shouldn't ever go to waste.
I'd let him go.
- Kara, what do you say? - Antonio, I'm buying in.
You got a yes from me.
Okay, and before you speak,
acknowledge that I am acknowledging good music,
and you made some.
What in the world are you saying, Man?
Shut up.
You're through to Hollywood.
What is all this nonsense?
Yes! Take it! Go!
- My God. - Bye, Antonio.
Skiiboski, Baby.
Yes, Skiiblow, Skiiblow.
Skiiblowski.
Skiiblowski
Skiiboski, baby!
Yeah! Yeah!
This is not a joke.
That guy is serious.
I was shocked that that came out of his mouth.
I was shocked that he could even sing,
'cause it was like, oh, my god.
Believe me, it takes more than a shirt to explain.
Skiiboski, baby.
S-k-double-i-b-o.
You already know.
American Idol, next one. Yeah.
Skii-bo-ski!
Atlanta is moving along nicely.
But there are still hundreds left to audition.
Contestants spend a lot of hours waiting for their turn.
And many bring along a close friend to keep them company.
Oh, I'm loved.
I'm loved.
And back in the holding room,
we met two girls who knew the meaning
of best friends better than anyone.
Hey, I'm Carmen Turner. I'm 19.
And I'm Lauren Sanders, and I'm 18.
- And we are BFFs - For life.
Let's talk about the friendship here.
How long have you been friends?
We have been friends since...
third grade.
We spend every weekend together.
We're BFFs, remember?
What happens if somebody makes it and somebody doesn't?
That's not gonna happen.
You're both gonna make it.
Duh!
Simon and Randy...
if you let us go...
unforgivable!
Carmen and Lauren...
Need to go to Hollywood!
Hello.
- Hi. - Hello.
- How are you? - I'm starstruck.
- Are you starstruck? - Yeah.
- I'm Lauren. - And I'm Carmen. Carmela.
Are you guys sisters or best friends or...
We're best friends.
You guys get in trouble together, the two of you?
Too much trouble.
I bet, I bet.
We give our parents trouble.
Anyone who walks in here like that looks like
she's gonna get into some trouble.
Are you gonna sing together or what?
No, we have totally, totally,
totally different voices.
Okay, who's the better one?
You'll have to see.
- Well, who do you think? - We're the same.
We're equally...
I believe we're equally talented.
Okay. Annoying, annoying.
What are you gonna sing?
Mmm... my pants
- No, you're lying. - What?
I was just kidding.
Lauren, okay, you go first.
What are you gonna sing?
All right, I'll go ahead and tell you all,
I got a soft voice,
but you all are gonna love it.
- Okay. - I doubt that.
I'm so nervous, so I'm sorry.
Carmen, you just need to
stand away from Miss annoying.
I'm so nervous.
# I'm awake in the infinite #
# cold #
# but you sing to me #
# over and over and over again #
Okay, that was beautiful.
Okay, Carmen, your turn.
# where is your heart #
# 'cause I don't really #
# feel you #
# where is your heart #
# what I really want #
# is to believe you #
# is it so hard #
# to give me what I need #
# I want your heart to bleed #
# that's all I'm asking for #
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Come on back together, you two.
I think, Carmen,
you were obviously better than your friend.
Um, having said that,
I would be in a group, the two of you,
because you're really, really funny together.
- You are. - No, you are,
you're hysterical.
And then when one of you leaves the other one,
you become boring.
And then you're back together, and you're fun.
I'll practice all y'all want me to.
You should be in a group.
My nerves are getting to me so bad.
You could be like the ditz sisters or something.
- The what? - The what?
- Ditz sisters. - The ditzies?
'Cause you're ditzy.
- You could be the ditzies. - The ditz.
Randy, yes or no to Lauren?
I would say yes to Carmen and no to Lauren
Based on the vocals, honestly.
Please, please.
I'll practice. I promise.
All right. Okay, Kara?
Sweetie, Lauren, part of being best friends,
you gotta support your best friend,
'cause she did a little bit better than you.
I disagree.
I'd either want to go up together
or down in flames together.
No, if they're good friends,
they'll support each other no matter what.
Can I sing another song or something?
No, no, honey.
So wait, I gotta say, um,
yes to Carmen and no to Lauren.
I'm sorry, honey.
- Mary. - I'm gonna say yes to Carmen.
I'm so sorry. This is hard.
Well, look, if it's any comfort,
I would have said no to both of you.
Um, but right now, Carmen,
You're through.
This is gonna be really awkward for the two of you now.
Hug it out. Hug it out, hug it out.
Oh, guys.
Oh, this sucks!
Carmen, if it's any consolation,
I don't think you're going to
be away from her for too long, so...
You're going to Hollywood, Carmen!
Whoo!
She wasn't that bad, Carmen.
But you guys still be best friends, promise us.
Love each others forever.
I couldn't ask for a better friend in life.
I don't care what anybody says.
It's a lifetime friendship.
You don't find that.
It's all right, Darling.
- I'm sorry. - It's fine.
I'm proud of you.
You'll support each other.
# keep smiling #
# keep shining #
# knowing you can #
# always count on me #
How difficult was that for you?
I'm gonna support her 100% of the way.
Are you upset?
I'm fine, I'm glad for her.
A lot of mixed emotions.
I wouldn't have gotten this far without you, Lauren.
Don't worry about it.
Best friend I could ask for.
# that's what friends #
# are for #
Let's hope their friendship will continue
through these tough times.
And we will continue after a break.
Coming up, the sweet Georgia peaches turn sour.
# lovin' that man of mine #
Is that a motor or something going on in your throat?
It's like, "uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh."
And a street-tough cop blows away the judges.
You know, this is what I love about this job.
Welcome back to Atlanta.
We're over halfway through
the second day of auditions,
and right now, a batch of southern belles
are clanging in the room.
# tell me I'm crazy #
# maybe I know #
# and I just can't help #
# lovin' that man of mi-ine #
# and I, I #
Oh, god.
# will always love you #
# ooh ooh #
# and with #
# a broken wing #
# she carries her dreams #
- Should I stop? - Yes.
Do people tell you, sweetie,
you're a good singer?
Well, not really.
But I don't let them discourage me.
Is there a motor of something going on in your throat?
It's like, "uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh."
Why did you stop?
Because of your facial expressions.
- What were they like? - Dreadful.
# do re fa so la #
Huh?
I don't know what else to say.
That's all I needed to hear.
- Okay. - That's fine.
Well, then, we'll leave it at that.
So Simon's ears were now ringing.
A little migraine.
A little one?
So he stepped out for a minute,
leaving the rest of the panel
to take a few auditions on their own.
Or was he really just avoiding the next contestant?
I'm Bryan Walker.
I'm 25 years old.
I'm a police officer in Sevierville, Tennessee.
Favorite part of my job is just getting the chance
to go out and protect, one,
the people that I love in the town,
in the hometown that I've grown up in.
and, two, just to get a chance to help people out.
All right, Sir, you have a safe day.
- Make sure you buckle up. - All right.
If I do make it on to Hollywood,
I know it would completely change my life.
I love my job, but I really want to
get a chance to, uh, chase a dream.
When I see the judges,
I'm gonna show them exactly what I'm there to do,
which is sing, to win America over,
and be the next American Idol.
What's going on, ATL?
ATL! Come on, ATL.
How you doing?
Good. How are you?
So you are currently a police officer?
Yes, Sir. Sure am.
- Ah, serving and proud, right? - Yes, Sir.
- I like that. - That is good.
So what are you gonna sing?
I'm actually gonna sing Superstar
in the style of Ruben Studdard.
- You ready? - Sure.
# long ago #
# and, oh, so far away #
# I fell in love with you #
# before the second show #
# whoa oh oh oh oh #
Hmm.
# don't you remember #
# you told me you loved me #
# baby #
# and you said you'd be coming #
# back this way again #
# baby, baby, baby, baby #
# oh, baby #
# I love you #
# I really do #
God, you know, this is what I love about this job,
'cause this guy comes in, and you think,
"oh, here we go."
But you know what?
- That... was great. - Thank you.
This guy could sing, right?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I agree with Kara.
You know, the thing that I love the most about you,
you being a police officer,
you look nothing like what you sound like.
I love the fake out like that.
You know what I'm saying?
I do too.
The singing police officer is hot, Dude.
You... I... whew!
You can sing, man.
Thank you, I appreciate that.
You have the type of voice
where you don't have to try to prove anything.
It's just there.
I think we can expect the unexpected from Bryan.
- Yes! - That's what I'm feeling.
What do you think?
Yes! Hollywood for Bryan!
Yes, I say yes!
You're going to Hollywood. Welcome to Hollywood.
- Three yeses! Hollywood! - Thank you so much.
- You're awesome. - The singing police officer.
I like it, Man.
Hey.
I have never seen a policeman
so excited to get a ticket.
But our next contestant wasn't just
thinking about Hollywood.
He had someone special looming in his head.
Oh, wow, I'm...I'm very excited about performing
in front of Mary J. Blige.
Um, she's like a... she's an idol herself.
She's just this big superstar,
and I really want to meet her.
Today, no matter what the judges say,
I will respect their opinion and...
I love taking constructive criticism.
And that's what I plan to do.
# baby #
# I compare you to a kiss #
# from a rose on the gray #
# ooh, the more I hear of you #
# the stranger it feels, yeah #
# now that your rose #
# is in bloom #
# a light hits the gloom #
# on the gray #
Powerful, Lamar.
Randy.
Lamar, Man, I got mad love for you, Man, but...
that was kind of torturous, Man.
I mean, I, you know... torturous?
Pitch was all over the place.
It was like, I don't...Dog...
Can I do another song for you?
No, no, it's not that, Man.
I just don't think you're that good, Man.
Sweetie, you know, you're 19 years old.
- I'm 20. - Okay, 20.
Y... I'm not gonna say that you're a terrible singer.
I'm really shocked, 'cause that's not true.
Hold on, I'm not gonna say...
No, she said she's not saying that.
Dog, are you a good listener?
I am a very good listener.
Okay, so listen to us for a second.
It wasn't great.
There's a voice in there somewhere.
You need to do a lot of work.
I don't even know if you're really, for this level...
# la la la #
No, Dog. Dog, Dog, Dog...
Don't sing anything else.
Dog! Listen, I asked if you were a good listener,
and you keep singing.
I am, 'cause I... I just can't believe...
Lamar, let me give you one little bit of advice.
What is going on?
I want to just share something with you.
You have to find some humility
in order to do this and pull back...
I want to...
Listen, and stop trying to exalt yourself.
And that's what you're doing.
You're running, so just...
- relax. - You need to do the work, Sweetheart.
You haven't done the work yet. So let's take a vote.
Lamar, no.
I'm gonna say no, 'cause you're
not ready yet, Dog.
I feel your passion.
But see, you're not even listening.
# baby, I compare you to #
# a kiss from a rose #
Lamar, what are you doing?
You all mother.
Lamar, we're trying to help you.
I don't understand. I really don't understand.
Lamar, listen. Listen, Sweetie.
You're all telling me, basically, I can't sing.
- No, we said... - That's an insult to me.
Nobody said you couldn't sing.
Nobody said that.
It wasn't great today, Dog.
You're not ready for this level.
- Are you serious? - Yes.
We're trying to find the best... you weren't the best.
We are trying to help you Honey, we're not trying to hurt you.
# la la la la la la #
Honey, right off the bat.
It's just...
# la la la #
# la la la la la la #
Work on that vibrato, Dog.
You all,
Mother.
Oh! That's... that's not...
Oh, really? We love you!
Mother!
That is not cool.
Just the whole damn American Idol show.
Mary J. Blige, all that.
That can't sing, neither.
She can't sing a lick.
Ooh, I started ducking,
'Cause I didn't know he was...
I started acting like...
Whack singers!
'Cause I didn't know
if he was gonna pull out a gun or what.
And who is Kara? Who is she?
I ain't never heard of that.
I wish Paula was here.
Randy, I thought you were gonna get up and...
I started getting my duck ready.
Get my duck ready!
Mary J. Blige said I can't sing.
That can't sing a lick!
He's crazy, Man.
Mary, that boy is crazy right there.
That boy is crazy right there.
What are you looking for? All right, this whole American Idol thing ain't
# la la la #
# la la #
# ha la #
Y'all!
It's American Idol coming
Ain't! The mother!
Still to come, we're wrapping things up in the ATL.
And our last audition proves to be, uh...
You'll have to watch it for yourself.
I have a horrible feeling that song could be a hit.
After the break.
Welcome back.
We're wrapping things up in Atlanta.
But before the Georgia sun sets,
we've got one last audition to show you.
Hello.
Your name is Larry Platt?
My name's General Larry Platt, yes.
- A general? - General Larry Platt.
Oh, you're a General, okay.
I want to sing my song called Pants On The Ground.
Pants On The Ground?
Pants On The Ground.
Okay, what's it about?
People need to pull their pants up.
All right.
Okay. Ready when you are.
- Okay, ready? - 1, 2, 3.
# pants on the ground #
# lookin' like a fool #
# with your pants #
# on the ground #
# with the gold in your mouth #
# hat turned sideways #
# pants hit the ground #
# call yourself a cool cat #
# lookin' like a fool #
# walkin' downtown with #
# your pants on the ground #
# get it up, hey #
# get your pants #
# off the ground #
# lookin' like a fool #
# walkin', talkin' with #
# your pants on the ground #
# get it up, hey #
# get your pants #
# off the ground #
# lookin' like a fool #
# with your pants #
# on the ground #
# gold in the mouth #
Okay. Okay!
Thank you.
# talkin' with your pants on the ground #
# boom, yeah #
Whoa! Careful.
# lookin' like a fool #
# with your pants #
# on the ground #
# with the gold in your mouth #
# hat turned sideways #
# pants hit the ground #
Larry, Larry...
Larry Larry...
Thank you.
Larry, what was that song called?
Pants on the ground.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
Positive?
You know, I have a horrible feeling
that song could be a hit.
Yeah. I'm gonna get my pants,
and I'm gonna buy some belts after this.
Yeah. Yeah, a lot of belts.
- Larry, can I ask you a question? - Yes.
- How old are you? - 62 years old.
What? 62 years old.
Good for you.
This year'll be my birthday on the 27th.
Okay, the only slight problem, Larry,
is that you're a little bit over the age limit,
which is 28.
But I don't think this is gonna be
the last we hear about you.
I have a feeling about you, Larry.
And we learned something today, Larry.
You know what we learned?
# pants on the ground #
Both: # pants on the ground #
# lookin' like a fool with #
# your pants on the ground #
Larry, thank you.
I'm now going to buy a belt.
With our pants pulled up and our belts tightened,
we say good-bye to Atlanta.
We gave out 25 golden tickets
and found some amazing talent.
And we learned a very important lesson.
# pants on the ground #
# you lookin' like a fool #
# with your pants #
# on the ground #
# with the gold in your mouth #
# hat turned sideways #
Yes!
Consensus, Atlanta.
Gang, how'd we do?
# hey, get your pants #
# off the ground #
I'm going to Hollywood!
- What'd you think of Mary? - Very harsh.
I think this show has changed you.
You know what? I think so too.
# call yourself a cool cat #
# lookin' like a fool #
# walkin', talkin' with #
# your pants on the ground #
# gold in your mouth #
Both: # with your hat #
# turned sideways #
# pants hit the ground #
# walkin', talkin' #
# with your pants #
# on the ground, get it up #
- Is that an original? - Right.
All right.
All: # pants on the ground #
# pants on the ground #
# lookin' like a fool #
# with your pants #
# on the ground #
# Hollywood, Hollywood #
# let's go to Hollywood #
Hey!
Hollywood.
Hollywood, you got it.
All right, that is Atlanta.
We move on.
Pack the bags, roll 'em out.
That's a wrap.
A real superstar, Ryan.
Pants on the ground.
General Larry Platt, out.
Next week, we encounter one of our biggest Idol audition crowds ever.
As idol takes on the midwest, Chicago-style.
# ah, ah, yeah #
Along the way, we'll hear some amazing voices...
# don't you be usin' #
# every day #
100 million percent yes.
See some familiar faces...
I remember this girl.
And make some new friends.
Get the out of my face.
As the windy city talent...
# aah #
No.
- blows the judges away. - Whoa!
Join us next week as
American Idol rolls through Chicago.
# aaah #
Do you find when you sing at home,
a lot of animals turn up outside the house?
Stop it!