Yes?
For you, milady.
The Village Mole far?
Sansa.
Lady Brienne.
When I heard that escaped
Winterfell, I feared the worst.
You have no idea how
I am happy to see her unharmed.
Ilesa?
What are you doing here?
I came with the Knights
Valley to help her.
Are camped in Moat Cailin at this time.
To help me?
You knew about Ramsay?
If you did not know, he is an idiot.
If you know, he is my enemy.
I wonder
our wedding night?
He never hurt my face.
He needed my face,
Ned Stark's daughter's face.
But the rest...
He did what he wanted with the rest...
As long as he could give him an heir.
What do you think he did?
I can not imagine...
What do you think you did to me?
Lady Sansa did you
a question.
He hit you.
Yes, he liked that.
What else you think you did?
- Sansa, I...
- What else?
He cut?
Perhaps he knew about Ramsay.
Do not know.
I thought I knew
secrets of all.
I made a mistake...
A horrible mistake.
I underestimated a stranger.
Women should not talk
about the other things he did...
But I imagine that owners
brothels speak of them all the time.
I can still feel.
Not in my heart,
still hurts me a lot.
I still feel what he did
my body right here, right now.
I feel...
A lot.
- You said you would protect me.
-.  And protect
- You must believe me.
- I do not believe you anymore.
I do not need you anymore.
You can not protect me.
Do not get or protect yourself
to ask Brienne to kill him.
Why should not kill him?
Want to beg for my life
?
If this is what you want, I beg.
I'll do anything you ask
and in my power...
And if you want to die
here and now?
So, I will die.
You saved me from the monsters
who killed my family...
And gave me the other monsters
who killed my family.
Return to Moat Cailin.
My brother and I will resume
north. I never want to see it.
I would do anything to undo
what they did to you.
I know I can not.
Do you allow me to say
one more thing before you go?
His uncle,
Brynden the Blackfish...
He joined the remnants of the forces
Tully and resumed Riverrun.
Should look for him.
You may need
a loyal army to you.
I have an army.
The army of his brother.
Half brother.
Not ready.
Should go home before
it is too late.
It will never be one of us...
Lady Stark.
She's right.
None of the Faceless Men
born lords and ladies.
Began as slaves in the mines of
Valyria.
- Who was the first?
- He was nobody.
The God of Many Faces you
taught how to hide his face...
And how to give the "gift."
The man taught others
in exchange for their services.
Many served,
more gifts were given.
So all teachers
and foremen went away...
And Men
Faceless fled.
Where do you go?
Here.
They founded the Free City of Bravos
and built this house.
These are the faces that used
when they were alive...
When not used other.
The first
Faceless Men.
Now the girl is one of them,
if the girl you want.
The girl has no desire
.
Who?
An actress
called Lady Crane.
It acts in the theater of
Sheelba Square.
To the girl was given
a second chance.
There will be a third.
One way or another, one
face will be added to the wall.
Murdered by a wild boar.
The big hairy vagrant.
He sank his fangs in my gut...
And quickly, do not exist anymore.
Come, father,
must lie in bed.
I love you, Dad.
Please do not die.
Shut up, you pig!
Cersei, more wine.
I feel the winter winds
licking the earth.
And our son alone
so cold that throne...
Without a guiding hand.
Who will teach you strength?
Who will teach you free?
Who will elec
when it's time to learn...
- To look into the darkness?
- Ned Stark serve.
Now, bring me more wine.
What happened here anyway?
He brought him here, Ned Stark...
Because you are the person
brighter land.
You should be king of all
us and I should be your hand.
We, Northern men are good
in keeping people in the law.
I ask permission,
but it stinks too.
I die!
And I must lie down in this place.
No!
I'm about to go.
- You will be a Hand of Joffrey?
- The Iron Throne is what I demand.
- You can not.
- I can.
- Can.
- Do not dare.
- I dare, yes.
- The line of succession.
- What does it mean?
- The right progression.
- Legal rise.
- What does it mean?
Move, give me my chair
and there will be no problem.
We had a hung tract.
Beginning to think it is not reliable.
Save my father.
You really should.
Kill the man
will not do any good.
- Save it, please.
- Show him mercy.
Show people
as a good king should be.
Good people should relax.
The friend of my father
should be forgiven...
Father! No!
Father!
Do not worry.
Everything is good.
I have here a decree
my father, Tywin Lannister...
The richest man summer.
He proclaims me the King's Hand.
The position is mine forever.
And I have your permission
to marry Sansa.
What I have high,
compensate with appetite.
Let's forget
your predicament...
And rehearse our wedding night.
It is a wart.
Two  warts.
I have two warts
on my penis.
Do not worry, love.
They desaperecem
in five or six years.
Wash it, honey. Fede much.
It may be better, Bianca,
dear. Must be.
I have two lines.
There are small stakes.
- You do not convinced.
- Not convinced?
What you need is someone
that do believe.
Do not complained
me last night.
Wine would, Lady Crane?
Rum tasting, Bobono.
Need to know if we will be close.
Of course we will be close.
It's just a matter of time.
To our children.
- With his talent.
- And your dirty mind.
Girl poison rum.
Lady Crane
is the only one who drinks.
If the girl could use
one of the faces of the wall...
The girl is not ready.
She's a good actress.
I've heard.
It looks like a decent woman.
Death only comes to bad
and ignores the good?
No.
Who wants her dead?
It does not matter.
The price was paid.
The youngest actress.
She's jealous because
Lady Crane's best.
Girl must decide whether
serve the God of Many Faces.
Girl decided.
A servant does not ask questions.
No! No!
It was you.
You did
the White Walkers.
We were at war.
We were being massacred.
Our trees
sacred cut.
We had to defend ourselves.
Who?
From you.
Of men.
We speak in the presence
the Drowned God.
In your name we gather today...
To choose a new king as our leader.
Who claims?
I am Yara Greyjoy...
Daughter of Balon Greyjoy...
King of the Iron Islands.
I claim the Throne of Sal.
We have never had a queen.
Never.
There are many things
ever did.
Never leave
our mark on the world.
The great lords of Westeros
are not interested in us...
Until our small invasions
go through their kingdoms...
And become a nuisance.
And in the crush.
They dominate us...
Humiliate us...
And return to forget
we exist.
Yes!
- We are a people of the sea.
- Yes!
Our God is God of the sea.
Yes!
When Queen
build a fleet...
- There will be queen!
- Not finished!
Yes, finished!
A woman not in the lead.
Not when the heir
the Balon own back.
I'm Theon Greyjoy...
Last living son
Balon Greyjoy.
And it is their legitimate ruler.
Yes!
Those who sailed with her
and there are many of you here...
Know who she is.
Yes!
- It is a robber.
- Yes!
- She's a warrior.
It is an iron woman!
Yes!
Will not find a better leader.
This is our queen.
Yara! Yara! Yara!
I am Euron Greyjoy.
Claim the Throne of Sal.
Hostess.
Sobrinho.
Small Theon.
I heard you could
ruin everything.
Captured a castle
he could not keep.
He was taken prisoner.
Until I heard you have no penis.
This explains why
supports a woman as king.
When she returned, Uncle?
A few days ago.
I had to do some things.
Outstanding things.
I'm glad you're here.
Now I know what I'll do
first as queen.
Run man
who killed my father.
I killed.
I killed him.
I threw a bridge
rope and saw him fall.
It did not take us anywhere...
And would remain so
if not for me.
No one loved him.
No one wanted to follow him.
It took us two wars
we could not win.
I apologize to all of you
not have killed him years ago.
It would have been difficult.
I was not here.
I heard you been loitering
the world having a great time.
Loitering?
That's what you say when
a penis is cut?
The great lords of Westeros
taught him those words?
You were not here.
Yara was here.
Being Iron Man.
Leading men of iron.
Preparing for the
lead to glory.
How you do it?
I will build the largest fleet
the world has ever seen.
Good idea...
But I who build
the Iron Fleet...
Because I know how to use it.
I've been around the world.
I saw more things
all of you together.
And across the sea...
There is a person who hates
the great lords of Westeros...
Much as we do.
Someone with a great army,
three great dragons...
And no husband.
I will build a fleet...
Will "wander" up there
and give it to Daenerys Targaryen...
With my big cock.
- Tempt the Queen of Dragons?
- Not to beguile.
The Iron Fleet to seduce.
And together, we will take
the Seven Kingdoms.
I was not born to be king.
I paid the iron price...
And here I am.
Euron! Euron! Euron! Euron!
What Euron his servant, born
again the sea as you.
Bless him with salt.
Bless it with stone.
Bless it with steel.
Listen to the waves.
Listen to God.
He speaks to us and says...
Euron Greyjoy is the only king.
Let the sea wash
its follies and vanities.
Let the old Euron drown.
Let your lungs
fill with seawater.
Let the fish eat
the scales from their eyes.
What you are dead
can not die...
But returns to rise,
harder and stronger.
What is dead
can not die.
Where are my nephews?
Let's kill them.
They stole our best
boats.
Will not be enough
to save them.
Get back to their homes.
Cut all the trees
find.
Serrem wood
and start building.
I want all men
bending beams.
I want all women
winding linen for masts.
Build thousand ships
and give them this world.
I bani, twice.
You came back twice.
And you saved my life.
So, I can not
welcome you back...
And I can not send him away.
You should send me away.
Is there a cure?
I do not know.
How long does it take?
I do not know well.
But I've seen what happens when
progresses.
I'll finish everything before.
Sorry.
Sorry, really.
Do not apologize.
All I ever wanted was
serve it.
Tyrion Lannister was right.
I love.
Always will.
Goodbye, khaleesi.
Do not leave your queen...
Jorah, the Andalo.
It was not released yet.
You swore loyalty.
Sworn to obey my commands
for the rest of your life.
Well, I order
to find a cure...
Wherever you are
in this world.
I order you to heal...
, Then return to me.
When taking the Seven Kingdoms...
Need you by my side.
In the last fortnight since
our pact with the Masters...
How many murders were committed...
The Sons of the Harpy?
No.
How many Masters were killed by
free men?
Two... but it was the day of the covenant.
Since then, nothing.
It is safe to say that peace reigned.
For now.
It is the best we have
in our profession.
It's not enough.
We were
edge of civil war...
I say it's a good start.
It's not enough
Meereen to have peace.
Need to know that Daenerys
is responsible for it.
The Sons of the Harpy
have a good story.
Resist foreign invaders
.
Our Queen has
a better story.
Mother of Dragons,
breaker chains and...
Everything.
They know who brought them freedom.
Yes, but they know who
gave them security?
Who put an end to violence?
We need someone
they trust...
Someone know that can not be bought or influenced
.
It looks like a hero.
Where to find him?
Who said it would be "it"?
You are in the presence
Kinvara...
High Priestess of the Temple
Red Volantis...
The Flame of Truth...
The Light of Wisdom...
First
Servant of the Lord of Light.
Welcome to Meereen.
That's all I know Valyrian.
Thank you for coming here.
I've tried and I know
travel can be uncomfortable.
The truth is that we need
your help.
We expected at least persuade her to...
Do not need to persuade me.
I came to help.
Born Daenerys of the Storm
is who was promised.
The fire she was reborn
to remake the world.
Yes.
It freed the slaves
chains...
And crucified the Masters
for their sins.
Yes, she did.
Your dragons are
fire made of flesh...
The Lord's gift of light.
But I have heard that before, right?
In Long Bridge Volantis.
The cleanse dragons
thousands of non-believers...
Burning their sins
and bodies.
Preferably flirted
purify many non-believers.
The Mother of Dragons has
followers of different faiths.
You want your queen
be honored and accepted.
And while no
want their advisers...
Are revered and heeded.
I'm glad to "heeded".
I will call
my most eloquent priests.
They will tell everyone.
Daenerys was sent to lead the people
against the darkness...
This war and great
war that will follow.
Excellent.
A man named Stannis Baratheon
was anointed...
As the chosen one of its priestesses.
It also
had a glorious destiny.
He attacked Port Royal
and was defeated...
For this man beside me.
I heard that he had been defeated
again...
This time in Winterfell...
And this time forever.
We would appreciate any support
which could give the queen.
I find it hard to
a fanatic admit a mistake.
That is what
be a fanatic, no?
You are always right.
It is the Lord's will.
But men and women
make mistakes.
Until honest servants of the Lord.
And you, a servant of the Lord
honest...
Why should trust
on you to find out more...
The priestess
who advised Stannis?
My friend is skeptical of religion,
but faithfully support the queen.
All are what they are, and are
where they are for a reason.
Things terrible
happen for a reason.
See what happened to you,
Lord Varys, when I was little.
If not for his mutilation
by a sorcerer second...
Would not be here...
Helping the Lord Chosen
bring your light to the world.
The knowledge gave him power.
But there is so much
do not know.
Remember
what he heard that night...
When the sorcerer played their parts
on fire?
You heard a voice from the flames.
Do you remember?
I must tell you
what the voice said?
I must tell you the name
who spoke?
We serve the same queen.
If you are your true friend,
has nothing to fear from me.
He saw me, the King of the Night!
He saw me!
It touched.
I do not know. It was close, but...
He knows he's here.
Will come after you.
But he can not enter.
It can now.
Your brand is you.
You must leave all of you.
Come on, Hodor,
help me with the sled.
Hodor.
Sorry. It was not on purpose.
The time has come.
Time for what?
For you to be me.
But...
I'm ready?
No.
We can not defend the north of
Walkers and the southern Boltons.
To survive
need Winterfell...
And to take Winterfell,
we need more men.
Outside the Starks and the Boltons,
the most powerful in North...
Are Umbers, the Karstarks,
and Manderlys.
The Umbers and Karstarks already
are in favor of the Boltons.
What it is not good for us.
The Umbers gave Rickon
to our enemies.
I hope they die.
But Karstarks
allied to Ramsay...
Without knowing they had no choice.
Sorry, but you know what
one Stark beheaded their father.
I think we can not
rely on them too.
You know well
the North, Sir Davos?
Very little, my lady.
My father said that Northerners are different.
More loyal...
More suspicious of outsiders.
Can be loyal...
But how many were
against the Boltons...
When betrayed your family?
I may not know
the North, but I know men.
They are like any
in the world...
And even the bravest...
Not want to see their wives and children
flayed...
For a lost cause.
If Jon is convince them
to fight at your side...
They need to believe
is a fight that will win.
There are three
homes in North...
Glover, Mormont, Cerwyn...
Mazin, Hornwood.
And two dozen more.
Together, the sum is equal
others.
We can start small and increase
.
The North remembers.
He remembers the Stark name.
The people risk everything Porto
White to Ramsay House.
I do not doubt.
But Jon is not named Stark.
No, but I have.
Jon is the son of Ned Stark
as Ramsay is Roose Bolton.
And we have Tullys.
There are northerners, but the
support against the Boltons.
I did not know yet
had an army.
My uncle, the Blackfish, the
rebuilt and resumed Riverrun.
How do you know?
Ramsay received a crow before
I escape from Winterfell.
That's good.
The Blackfish is a legend.
Your support would mean a lot.
Stark, Tully,
some other houses...
Is beginning to smell victory.
I swore to protect her, milady.
You heard them.
We need more men
and my uncle has an army.
We can send a raven to Blackfish.
Ramsay can intercept.
Must be you. Go to Riverrun.
My uncle will speak to you
and know how to talk to him.
What?
I do not like to leave her alone.
With Jon?
No, he.
It seems reliable.
A little thoughtful.
It is perhaps understandable.
Yet others.
Davos and Red Woman...
Helped a man kill his own brother...
With blood magic.
And when Stannis
paid for his crime, where were they?
Why there looking
a better leader.
And that Wild bearded...
Jon is not Tormund.
Jon is not Davos,
the Red Woman or Stannis.
Jon is Jon.
He's my brother. He will keep me safe
. I trust him.
So why lie when
asked about Riverrun?
New dress?
I sewed the same.
You like him?
Yes, it's...
I like the part of the wolf.
Good,
because I did it for you.
I did like what Dad used to use
.
Well, as I recall.
Thank you, Sansa.
You're welcome.
Do not drop,
while I'm gone.
I will do my best.
Good luck.
We should close the gate,
Lord Commander?
I am Lord Coman...
Yes...
Close the damn door.
Can we go
home now, Hodor.
Not home, but some
place than a cave.
Hodor.
Eat something
than moss.
I want an egg.
How would you like?
Cooked?
Fried with butter?
Hodor.
With  Bacon  and sausage.
Take Bran and run!
Bran. Bran, wake up.
- Bran.
- Hodor. Hodor.
Bran, wake up.
- The gods keep you on the road.
- Calm. Caution.
Hodor.
Hodor. Hodor.
Help me!
Go!
Remember that is a Stark.
Behave with dignity in the Valley...
And try to stay away from fights.
Yes, father.
But if you have to fight...
Win.
Bran! Bran, wake up!
Bran!
Bran! Bran, wake up.
- Hodor. Hodor.
- Bran! Bran, wake up!
You must wake up.
- We need Hodor.
- Hodor. Hodor.
Bran, Hodor need.
Bran, you must agree.
We need Hodor.
Hodor. Hodor.
Bran, all die!
Bran, wake up!
We will die all!
Bran! Bran!
Bran, you must agree.
We need Hodor.
Hodor. Hodor.
Control Hodor now!
Bran, wake up.
We need Hodor.
Control Hodor now! Now!
Listen to your friend, Brandon.
Hodor. Hodor.
Summer!
Go.
Go!
It's time.
Let me.
What are you doing?
Go!
Hodor, fast!
Hodor!
Hold the door!
- Hold the door
- Wylis!
What?
Hold the door!
Come on, son.
Hodor!
Hold the door!
Hodor! Hodor!
Translated by Google translator
from Portuguese.