1
00:00:43,300 --> 00:00:45,340
Is there any news of Sybil?

2
00:00:45,340 --> 00:00:48,580
She's still not coming. She
insists they can't afford it.

3
00:00:48,580 --> 00:00:50,580
Mr Travis, can we move forward?

4
00:00:51,140 --> 00:00:53,940
If I could just ask you to
come down the aisle again?

5
00:00:55,220 --> 00:00:57,220
Can we get the troops organised?

6
00:00:57,300 --> 00:00:59,300
That means me.

7
00:00:59,620 --> 00:01:03,220
It seems rather hard on poor old
Travis when he's doing all the work,

8
00:01:03,220 --> 00:01:05,060
but the Archbishop gets the glory.

9
00:01:05,060 --> 00:01:07,460
Papa was the one who wanted
a prince of the church.

10
00:01:07,460 --> 00:01:09,220
I'd have settled for Travis.

11
00:01:09,220 --> 00:01:12,460
Is there really no way we can get
Sybil over? It seems ridiculous.

12
00:01:12,460 --> 00:01:14,620
On the contrary, it's a relief.

13
00:01:14,620 --> 00:01:18,140
Branson is still an object
of fascination for the county.

14
00:01:18,140 --> 00:01:22,500
We'll ask him here when we can prepare
the servants and manage it gently.

15
00:01:22,660 --> 00:01:24,900
He's making a problem where none exists.

16
00:01:24,900 --> 00:01:28,060
No-one could care less whether
Branson's at the wedding or not.

17
00:01:28,260 --> 00:01:30,820
You must think country life
more exciting than it is

18
00:01:30,820 --> 00:01:34,980
if you imagine people don't care when an
earl's daughter runs off with the chauffeur.

19
00:01:34,980 --> 00:01:38,740
She has run off with the chauffeur
and they'll have to get used to it.

20
00:01:38,740 --> 00:01:42,780
Mr Travis, are we ready? Any
moment, Your Grace. Any moment.

21
00:01:44,220 --> 00:01:46,220
Can we... Please.

22
00:02:00,100 --> 00:02:03,020
That treacle tart just hit the
spot. Thank you, Mrs Patmore.

23
00:02:03,020 --> 00:02:05,860
So, Mrs Hughes and Anna are
getting the place ready to let?

24
00:02:05,860 --> 00:02:07,700
That is the plan.

25
00:02:07,700 --> 00:02:09,980
I'm surprised Anna held on to that house.

26
00:02:10,380 --> 00:02:13,100
I thought they'd confiscated
the profits of murder.

27
00:02:13,100 --> 00:02:16,260
Mr Bates had the wisdom to
transfer it to her before the trial.

28
00:02:16,260 --> 00:02:18,220
I don't think I'd have allowed it.

29
00:02:18,220 --> 00:02:21,020
Then we must be grateful you
were not the presiding judge.

30
00:02:21,540 --> 00:02:25,540
I still think it's funny, given
that he's a convicted murderer.

31
00:02:25,540 --> 00:02:29,300
May I remind you, Mr Barrow, that in
this house Mr Bates is a wronged man

32
00:02:29,300 --> 00:02:32,860
seeking justice. If you have any
problems with that definition,

33
00:02:32,860 --> 00:02:34,860
I suggest you eat in the yard.

34
00:02:42,100 --> 00:02:46,340
I suppose you agree with Robert. Not
for the first time, you suppose wrongly.

35
00:02:47,860 --> 00:02:51,500
The family must never be
a topic of conversation.

36
00:02:51,500 --> 00:02:54,780
I'm afraid Sybil's already made
the Crawleys a permanent topic.

37
00:02:54,780 --> 00:02:56,820
All the more reason.

38
00:02:56,820 --> 00:02:59,140
If we can show the county
he can behave normally,

39
00:02:59,140 --> 00:03:01,020
they will soon lose interest in him.

40
00:03:01,020 --> 00:03:03,620
And I shall make sure he behaves normally

41
00:03:03,620 --> 00:03:06,860
because I shall hold his hand
on the radiator until he does.

42
00:03:07,260 --> 00:03:10,860
I don't know this young man aside
from 'Good morning' and 'Good night',

43
00:03:10,860 --> 00:03:14,460
but he strikes me as a very
interesting addition to the family.

44
00:03:14,460 --> 00:03:18,660
Oh, here we go. And why should
he be normal as you call it?

45
00:03:18,660 --> 00:03:21,820
I say he should come
here and fight his corner.

46
00:03:21,820 --> 00:03:23,940
I like a man of strong beliefs.

47
00:03:25,100 --> 00:03:26,940
I think I'll send them the money.

48
00:03:26,940 --> 00:03:30,660
Please don't. Robert's expressly
forbidden it. He'd be furious.

49
00:03:33,020 --> 00:03:34,860
But it can't be as bad as...

50
00:03:36,180 --> 00:03:38,940
Look, I'll come and see you, tomorrow.

51
00:03:39,380 --> 00:03:41,380
No, I insist.

52
00:03:41,700 --> 00:03:43,700
Right. Goodbye.

53
00:03:46,260 --> 00:03:48,140
Papa... What's the matter?

54
00:03:48,860 --> 00:03:51,660
Nothing's the matter.
What should be the matter?

55
00:03:58,300 --> 00:04:00,780
How was London? We got it all done.

56
00:04:00,780 --> 00:04:04,060
But I couldn't have managed
without my helper. Have you eaten?

57
00:04:04,060 --> 00:04:05,820
We had a bite on the train.

58
00:04:05,820 --> 00:04:07,900
Well, sit down anyway. Have a cup of tea.

59
00:04:08,460 --> 00:04:13,460
I'll start on the final list
for the wedding tomorrow morning.

60
00:04:13,460 --> 00:04:16,820
I've got the last of the wine
deliveries coming on Tuesday.

61
00:04:16,820 --> 00:04:19,940
How will you manage
without a footman? I agree.

62
00:04:19,940 --> 00:04:21,900
But I haven't time to find one now.

63
00:04:21,900 --> 00:04:25,900
I've had a letter from my sister
asking after a job for her son and -

64
00:04:25,900 --> 00:04:29,380
Miss O'Brien, we are about
to host a society wedding.

65
00:04:29,380 --> 00:04:32,300
I have no time for
training young hobbledehoys.

66
00:04:32,620 --> 00:04:34,620
(BELL RINGING)

67
00:04:35,300 --> 00:04:37,300
Her ladyship is ringing.

68
00:04:43,780 --> 00:04:45,660
Well, I don't see why not.

69
00:04:45,660 --> 00:04:48,540
I'll ask his lordship
when... There you are.

70
00:04:48,540 --> 00:04:50,940
So I'll ask you now. Ask me what?

71
00:04:50,940 --> 00:04:54,180
Carson's in need of a footman
and O'Brien has a candidate.

72
00:04:54,180 --> 00:04:57,020
Alfred. Alfred Nugent, my
lord. He's a good worker.

73
00:04:57,020 --> 00:04:59,020
I think it sounds perfect.

74
00:04:59,700 --> 00:05:04,140
Robert? Whatever you say. My dear,
I have to go up to London tomorrow.

75
00:05:04,140 --> 00:05:06,980
I'll be catching the early
train. That's very sudden.

76
00:05:06,980 --> 00:05:10,060
Do you want them to open the
house? No, I'll come straight back.

77
00:05:10,060 --> 00:05:13,100
What are you going for? It's
nothing to bother you with.

78
00:05:27,860 --> 00:05:30,100
It's all there, every entry.

79
00:05:32,140 --> 00:05:35,180
Where did you find the
book? Behind the bureau.

80
00:05:35,180 --> 00:05:37,380
We moved it out to clean and there it was.

81
00:05:38,500 --> 00:05:40,500
Vera must have dropped it or something.

82
00:05:40,500 --> 00:05:42,380
So what do you want me to do?

83
00:05:42,380 --> 00:05:44,380
Make notes on all the names.

84
00:05:44,940 --> 00:05:46,940
Close friend, relation.

85
00:05:47,180 --> 00:05:49,180
Workmate, tradesman, and so on.

86
00:05:49,380 --> 00:05:53,060
Then I'll copy those and I'll send
them with the book to Mr Murray.

87
00:05:53,820 --> 00:05:56,980
Haven't you anything
better to do? I have not.

88
00:05:57,740 --> 00:06:02,460
Because I'd rather work to get you free
than dine with the King at Buckingham Palace.

89
00:06:05,780 --> 00:06:07,780
So what news have you got?

90
00:06:08,500 --> 00:06:10,500
What news could I have in here?

91
00:06:11,420 --> 00:06:13,380
Oh, I've acquired a new cellmate.

92
00:06:13,380 --> 00:06:15,380
To be honest, I'm not sure about him.

93
00:06:16,820 --> 00:06:20,180
Well, just remember what
my mother used to say.

94
00:06:20,700 --> 00:06:22,700
Never make an enemy by accident.

95
00:06:24,340 --> 00:06:28,060
Now, do you think you can get the
notes done before my next visit?

96
00:06:29,340 --> 00:06:31,100
I don't see what can come of it.

97
00:06:31,500 --> 00:06:33,500
Probably nothing.

98
00:06:33,500 --> 00:06:35,900
And my next idea will
probably lead to nothing.

99
00:06:35,900 --> 00:06:37,900
And the next, and the next.

100
00:06:38,300 --> 00:06:40,780
But one day something will occur to us.

101
00:06:41,140 --> 00:06:43,020
And we'll follow it up.

102
00:06:43,020 --> 00:06:45,140
And the case against you will crumble.

103
00:06:46,860 --> 00:06:48,580
Do you never doubt?

104
00:06:48,580 --> 00:06:50,580
For just one minute.

105
00:06:51,700 --> 00:06:55,260
I wouldn't blame you. No.

106
00:06:55,860 --> 00:06:58,940
I don't doubt that the sun
will rise in the east either.

107
00:07:03,380 --> 00:07:05,380
You're too tall to be a footman.

108
00:07:05,940 --> 00:07:08,740
No footman should be over six foot one.

109
00:07:08,740 --> 00:07:11,940
That can't be, can it, since
he's already been taken on?

110
00:07:12,780 --> 00:07:16,900
Well, what have you done? I was a hotel
waiter after I was discharged from the army.

111
00:07:16,900 --> 00:07:21,340
But they've cut back. I think
that shows real initiative.

112
00:07:21,740 --> 00:07:24,180
I suppose he can speak for himself.

113
00:07:24,180 --> 00:07:26,180
Why? Is he on trial?

114
00:07:26,820 --> 00:07:30,380
This isn't an interview, is it?
Not when he's already got the job.

115
00:07:30,380 --> 00:07:32,660
No, it is not an interview, Miss O'Brien,

116
00:07:32,660 --> 00:07:35,860
but he is on trial and if he
cannot match our standards,

117
00:07:35,860 --> 00:07:38,740
he will be found guilty.
I mean to try, Mr Carson.

118
00:07:38,740 --> 00:07:40,740
As long as you do.

119
00:07:40,740 --> 00:07:42,860
Right, go upstairs and get settled in.

120
00:07:43,180 --> 00:07:46,540
Your aunt will hopefully
find you a livery that fits.

121
00:07:52,220 --> 00:07:56,460
Just at the start, so we've a
place to sleep after the honeymoon.

122
00:07:56,460 --> 00:07:58,340
You can't object to that.

123
00:07:58,340 --> 00:08:00,180
No, it's nice of them.

124
00:08:00,580 --> 00:08:04,300
Though I doubt I'll get used to taking
you to bed with your father watching.

125
00:08:04,300 --> 00:08:08,460
He's so relieved we're getting married, he
wouldn't mind if you carried me up naked.

126
00:08:08,460 --> 00:08:10,460
Careful. I might try it.

127
00:08:13,020 --> 00:08:15,180
I don't want to move to London or anything.

128
00:08:15,180 --> 00:08:17,580
I'm not kicking against the traces.

129
00:08:17,580 --> 00:08:19,380
Just testing their strengths.

130
00:08:19,380 --> 00:08:21,380
I want us to get to know each other.

131
00:08:22,420 --> 00:08:25,900
To learn about who we both are,
without everybody being there.

132
00:08:26,740 --> 00:08:28,700
Well, it's quite a big house.

133
00:08:28,700 --> 00:08:30,740
It's a lovely house.

134
00:08:30,740 --> 00:08:33,140
It's your home and I
want it to be my home too.

135
00:08:34,700 --> 00:08:36,700
Just not quite yet.

136
00:08:45,420 --> 00:08:48,660
Chancery Lane. Yes, sir.

137
00:08:52,780 --> 00:08:55,500
I've spoken to Frobisher and Curran

138
00:08:55,500 --> 00:08:59,260
and, since I am a trustee,
should the estate ever need one,

139
00:08:59,260 --> 00:09:01,380
we felt I ought to be the one to tell you.

140
00:09:02,020 --> 00:09:03,900
You make it sound very serious.

141
00:09:03,900 --> 00:09:07,540
I'm expressing myself badly
if you think it is not serious.

142
00:09:09,540 --> 00:09:12,460
Why did we invest so much?

143
00:09:12,460 --> 00:09:15,380
Lord Grantham, it was you
who insisted we should.

144
00:09:15,380 --> 00:09:17,540
If you remember, we advised against it.

145
00:09:17,540 --> 00:09:20,860
But war would mean a huge
expansion of railways everywhere.

146
00:09:20,860 --> 00:09:22,780
Every forecast was certain.

147
00:09:22,780 --> 00:09:25,340
Rail shares were bound to make a fortune.

148
00:09:25,340 --> 00:09:28,860
Many did. But your principal
holding, which was very large indeed,

149
00:09:28,860 --> 00:09:31,540
was in the Canadian Grand Trunk Line.

150
00:09:31,540 --> 00:09:35,420
It was the main railway in British
North America, for God's sake.

151
00:09:35,420 --> 00:09:38,540
It wasn't just me. Everyone
said we couldn't lose.

152
00:09:39,620 --> 00:09:42,380
We knew hard times were
coming for estates like Downton

153
00:09:42,380 --> 00:09:45,420
and this investment would make
it safe for the rest of time.

154
00:09:45,420 --> 00:09:47,580
Charles Hays was the presiding genius

155
00:09:47,580 --> 00:09:50,020
and since he died, the
management has not...

156
00:09:51,020 --> 00:09:54,820
The fact is, the company is
about to be declared bankrupt.

157
00:09:55,140 --> 00:09:59,260
And the line will be absorbed into
the Canadian National Railways scheme.

158
00:10:03,100 --> 00:10:06,020
Are you really telling me
that all the money has gone?

159
00:10:07,180 --> 00:10:10,700
I'm afraid so. The lion's
share of Cora's fortune?

160
00:10:20,540 --> 00:10:22,540
I won't give in, Murray.

161
00:10:23,420 --> 00:10:26,300
I've sacrificed too much
to Downton to give in now.

162
00:10:27,020 --> 00:10:28,980
I refuse to be the failure,

163
00:10:28,980 --> 00:10:32,300
the earl who dropped the
torch and let the flame go out.

164
00:10:32,300 --> 00:10:36,540
I hate to state the obvious, but if
there's not enough money to run it...

165
00:10:37,180 --> 00:10:39,020
Downton must go.

166
00:10:39,020 --> 00:10:42,100
Unless you break it up
and sell it off piecemeal.

167
00:10:42,100 --> 00:10:46,460
I couldn't do that. I have a
duty beyond saving my own skin.

168
00:10:47,260 --> 00:10:50,740
The estate must be a major
employer and support the house

169
00:10:50,740 --> 00:10:53,100
or there's no point to it. To any of it.

170
00:10:59,145 --> 00:11:01,145
Morning.

171
00:11:04,585 --> 00:11:06,585
Lady Edith...

172
00:11:12,665 --> 00:11:14,665
Hello.

173
00:11:14,985 --> 00:11:18,505
What are you doing here? I'm meeting
a train, but I'm too early. Oh.

174
00:11:18,505 --> 00:11:21,425
Oh. I mustn't hold you
up. I'm not doing anything.

175
00:11:22,025 --> 00:11:24,185
I thought I'd get away from wedding panic.

176
00:11:24,945 --> 00:11:28,225
Don't you like weddings?
Don't be silly. Of course I do.

177
00:11:28,625 --> 00:11:31,945
Only I've talked of clothes
and flowers and food and guests

178
00:11:31,945 --> 00:11:33,945
until I'm blue in the face.

179
00:11:34,225 --> 00:11:37,905
Yes, weddings can be reminders
of one's loneliness, can't they?

180
00:11:38,425 --> 00:11:40,345
Sorry. I don't know why I said that.

181
00:11:40,345 --> 00:11:42,145
So, how's it going?

182
00:11:42,145 --> 00:11:45,465
Is your grandmother coming over
from New York for it? She is.

183
00:11:45,745 --> 00:11:47,785
And Sybil... Is she here yet?

184
00:11:47,785 --> 00:11:51,145
As a matter of fact, she wasn't
coming. But I think she is now.

185
00:11:51,145 --> 00:11:52,985
Mary had a letter this morning.

186
00:11:52,985 --> 00:11:55,985
Papa doesn't know yet. He will be pleased.

187
00:11:55,985 --> 00:11:58,025
I do hope so.

188
00:11:59,665 --> 00:12:02,985
So you'll live at the big house
when you're back from honeymoon?

189
00:12:02,985 --> 00:12:04,985
Not live. Stay.

190
00:12:05,385 --> 00:12:07,865
We'll stay there until
we decide where to go.

191
00:12:08,225 --> 00:12:11,145
It'll be on the estate, I
should think, or in the village.

192
00:12:11,145 --> 00:12:13,145
Not here? No.

193
00:12:13,665 --> 00:12:17,025
But I shall expect you and Mrs
Bird to look after Mrs Crawley.

194
00:12:20,825 --> 00:12:22,865
You'll not be taking me with you, sir?

195
00:12:23,105 --> 00:12:27,465
Only I thought you'd be needing a
proper valet, once you're married.

196
00:12:28,425 --> 00:12:32,105
I've always thought of you as a
butler who helps out as a valet -

197
00:12:32,105 --> 00:12:35,025
not the other way round. I'd
be happy to be a valet, sir.

198
00:12:35,025 --> 00:12:38,425
Especially in the big house. We
won't be at the big house for long.

199
00:12:39,065 --> 00:12:42,865
To be honest, Molesley, I want to
live more simply after the wedding.

200
00:12:44,185 --> 00:12:47,625
And besides, Mother
absolutely relies on you.

201
00:12:48,465 --> 00:12:51,065
Well, that's very nice
to hear, sir. Thank you.

202
00:12:53,105 --> 00:12:54,985
You must be exhausted, my lord.

203
00:12:54,985 --> 00:12:57,625
You can't have spent more
than two hours in London.

204
00:12:57,625 --> 00:13:01,545
It was sufficient. The new footman
arrived while you were gone.

205
00:13:02,025 --> 00:13:04,065
What?

206
00:13:04,065 --> 00:13:07,345
Yes, he got the cable this
morning and came straight over.

207
00:13:08,465 --> 00:13:10,305
Very eager.

208
00:13:10,305 --> 00:13:12,225
And very tall.

209
00:13:12,225 --> 00:13:14,225
But when did...

210
00:13:14,545 --> 00:13:16,545
Never mind.

211
00:13:18,465 --> 00:13:20,625
Did you know about the new footman?

212
00:13:20,625 --> 00:13:22,625
Of course. He's already here.

213
00:13:22,785 --> 00:13:25,945
Why did no-one tell me? What do you mean?

214
00:13:25,945 --> 00:13:28,225
We talked about it last night. In my room.

215
00:13:28,425 --> 00:13:31,905
Well, nobody else must be
taken on. Absolutely no-one.

216
00:13:31,905 --> 00:13:33,905
Until things are settled.

217
00:13:34,105 --> 00:13:36,105
What things?

218
00:13:36,465 --> 00:13:39,625
How's the wedding going? I
suppose it's costing the earth?

219
00:13:39,625 --> 00:13:41,945
Mary was never going to marry on the cheap.

220
00:13:41,945 --> 00:13:44,785
Oh, no. Nothing must be done on the cheap.

221
00:13:47,665 --> 00:13:49,505
I feel quite nervous. Don't be.

222
00:13:49,505 --> 00:13:52,065
You've got the skill and
you've got the willingness.

223
00:13:52,065 --> 00:13:54,305
But he hasn't got the
experience. He's right.

224
00:13:54,305 --> 00:13:58,905
Pay no attention. You've a nice
manner. You're not vain like Thomas.

225
00:13:58,905 --> 00:14:00,905
They'll like that.

226
00:14:03,705 --> 00:14:05,665
What's the matter with you? I'm fed up.

227
00:14:05,665 --> 00:14:09,265
They promised me promotion. She
said they'd get a new kitchen maid

228
00:14:09,265 --> 00:14:11,065
and I'd be Mrs Patmore's assistant.

229
00:14:11,065 --> 00:14:13,825
If they promised, you should
withdraw your services.

230
00:14:13,825 --> 00:14:16,785
What do you mean? Like go on strike?

231
00:14:16,785 --> 00:14:18,785
But don't say I put you up to it.

232
00:14:22,265 --> 00:14:25,825
But what was in the letter? Just
that Sybil's coming after all.

233
00:14:25,825 --> 00:14:27,945
She'll be here on Wednesday for dinner.

234
00:14:27,945 --> 00:14:31,465
Will she be coming alone?
Don't make trouble, Mother.

235
00:14:32,745 --> 00:14:35,905
Can I do it? If you
wish, my lady. Of course.

236
00:14:36,665 --> 00:14:40,785
Are you really that tall? Yes, my lady.

237
00:14:41,665 --> 00:14:44,025
I thought you might have
been walking on stilts.

238
00:14:45,305 --> 00:14:47,225
When does Grandmama arrive?

239
00:14:47,225 --> 00:14:50,785
She gets into Liverpool on the 15th
- the day before the wedding

240
00:14:50,785 --> 00:14:53,425
I'm so looking forward to
seeing your mother again.

241
00:14:53,425 --> 00:14:57,225
When I'm with her I'm reminded
of the virtues of the English.

242
00:14:57,705 --> 00:15:00,345
But isn't she American? Exactly.

243
00:15:01,065 --> 00:15:02,945
Can I help myself?

244
00:15:02,945 --> 00:15:04,865
You want to as well, my lord?

245
00:15:04,865 --> 00:15:08,265
To be honest, I think you'll
find that we all do it as well.

246
00:15:09,145 --> 00:15:12,385
What do you think you're doing?
You're not in a hotel now.

247
00:15:14,905 --> 00:15:16,905
Did you train in a hotel?

248
00:15:16,905 --> 00:15:18,905
I did, ma'am.

249
00:15:19,345 --> 00:15:21,465
That will be useful. Won't it, Carson?

250
00:15:23,185 --> 00:15:25,225
Are you all set for the wedding?

251
00:15:25,225 --> 00:15:28,505
Of course he is. Carson's
motto is, 'Be prepared.'

252
00:15:28,745 --> 00:15:31,265
I'm afraid Baden-Powell has stolen it.

253
00:15:31,585 --> 00:15:33,585
But you have all the help you need?

254
00:15:33,905 --> 00:15:37,385
Well, I wouldn't fight the idea
of a second footman, my lady.

255
00:15:39,185 --> 00:15:43,265
I sometimes think it's time
we lived in a simpler way.

256
00:15:43,265 --> 00:15:45,625
I agree. Much cattle, much care.

257
00:15:45,625 --> 00:15:47,705
Always supposing we have the choice.

258
00:15:47,705 --> 00:15:51,265
Oh, don't say that. It's our
job to provide employment.

259
00:15:51,745 --> 00:15:53,825
An aristocrat with no servants

260
00:15:53,825 --> 00:15:56,585
is as much use to the
county as a glass hammer!

261
00:15:59,105 --> 00:16:03,065
I knew this would happen.
Typical. What's typical?

262
00:16:03,065 --> 00:16:06,985
That I'd wind up looking after
Mr Matthew. That's all I need.

263
00:16:06,985 --> 00:16:10,545
He hasn't thought it through.
I'm sorry to say, but he hasn't.

264
00:16:10,625 --> 00:16:13,065
Are you worried for your job, Mr Molesley?

265
00:16:13,065 --> 00:16:14,825
Me? Oh, heavens, no.

266
00:16:14,825 --> 00:16:18,225
No, no, no, I'm essential to
Mrs Crawley. She relies on me.

267
00:16:18,225 --> 00:16:20,985
That's what he said. Essential.

268
00:16:20,985 --> 00:16:24,265
Oh, yes, we're all essential.
Until we get sacked.

269
00:16:25,425 --> 00:16:29,265
How was it? Alfred was confused.

270
00:16:29,265 --> 00:16:32,545
He thought he'd been transported
to the Hotel Metropole.

271
00:16:33,345 --> 00:16:35,545
Cheer up. You'll get the hang of it.

272
00:16:35,545 --> 00:16:40,265
Will I? Oh, you're still here, Mr Molesley.

273
00:16:40,265 --> 00:16:43,385
I know. I only walked over
for a cup of tea and a chat.

274
00:16:43,385 --> 00:16:45,705
But I've outstayed my welcome. Nonsense.

275
00:16:45,705 --> 00:16:47,665
Why not have a bite with us?

276
00:16:47,665 --> 00:16:50,265
They won't be leaving
for a half hour or more.

277
00:16:50,265 --> 00:16:52,985
No, I'd better get back. I
wouldn't want them to get home

278
00:16:52,985 --> 00:16:55,825
and me not be there to let
them in. No, you wouldn't.

279
00:16:56,425 --> 00:16:58,425
Not when you're essential.

280
00:16:59,825 --> 00:17:01,785
Then why is he coming all the way here?

281
00:17:01,785 --> 00:17:04,865
Why not say it on the
telephone? I have no idea.

282
00:17:04,865 --> 00:17:07,545
If Mr Swire's lawyer wants
to see you and it's urgent,

283
00:17:07,545 --> 00:17:09,785
it means he's left you
something. I doubt it.

284
00:17:09,785 --> 00:17:11,665
I would have heard long before this.

285
00:17:11,665 --> 00:17:14,625
Anyway, I hope not. Why?

286
00:17:14,625 --> 00:17:16,825
Matthew. Do come on.

287
00:17:16,825 --> 00:17:19,145
The chauffeur's freezing
to death and so am I.

288
00:17:21,625 --> 00:17:23,785
Are you looking forward to the wedding?

289
00:17:23,785 --> 00:17:25,785
What do you think?

290
00:17:26,345 --> 00:17:28,545
I'm looking forward to all sorts of things.

291
00:17:28,945 --> 00:17:31,545
Don't make me blush. Matthew!

292
00:18:02,905 --> 00:18:04,905
Dearest Papa.

293
00:18:06,585 --> 00:18:09,345
Tell me, did you send the money?

294
00:18:09,625 --> 00:18:12,465
Please say yes. What money?

295
00:18:12,465 --> 00:18:14,465
Hello, Tom.

296
00:18:14,545 --> 00:18:16,545
Welcome to Downton.

297
00:18:16,705 --> 00:18:20,385
I hope I am welcome,
your ladyship. Of course.

298
00:18:21,265 --> 00:18:24,265
Alfred, would you take
the luggage for Mr Branson?

299
00:18:25,185 --> 00:18:26,985
There's tea in the library.

300
00:18:27,905 --> 00:18:29,905
Thank you.

301
00:18:38,425 --> 00:18:40,425
Hello, Mr Carson.

302
00:18:48,305 --> 00:18:52,105
Is that Mr Charkham I saw leaving? Yes.

303
00:18:52,105 --> 00:18:55,305
He said to make his apologies.
He was late for his train.

304
00:18:55,305 --> 00:18:57,305
What did he have to say for himself?

305
00:18:58,305 --> 00:19:00,305
I don't know where to start.

306
00:19:00,385 --> 00:19:05,665
Basically, it seems that Reggie Swire
did not wish to divide his fortune.

307
00:19:06,585 --> 00:19:10,345
So when Lavinia died, he made a
new will with a list of three heirs,

308
00:19:10,345 --> 00:19:12,665
of which I was the third.

309
00:19:13,585 --> 00:19:16,145
Why didn't the first name succeed?

310
00:19:16,145 --> 00:19:18,145
He died before Reggie.

311
00:19:18,345 --> 00:19:20,865
In the same epidemic that killed Lavinia.

312
00:19:21,305 --> 00:19:25,585
But at first they thought that the
second heir, a Mr Clive Pullbrook,

313
00:19:25,585 --> 00:19:27,585
would be easy to trace.

314
00:19:27,865 --> 00:19:29,865
How much money are we talking about?

315
00:19:30,625 --> 00:19:32,625
A lot.

316
00:19:32,905 --> 00:19:34,905
A huge amount. I had no idea.

317
00:19:35,185 --> 00:19:37,985
You could never have told
it from Reggie's way of life.

318
00:19:37,985 --> 00:19:39,985
Lucky Mr Pullbrook.

319
00:19:40,545 --> 00:19:42,545
This is it.

320
00:19:42,945 --> 00:19:45,465
Some time before Reggie's death,

321
00:19:45,465 --> 00:19:47,425
Pullbrook travelled to the East,

322
00:19:47,425 --> 00:19:50,265
to India, to some tea
plantations he owned there.

323
00:19:51,945 --> 00:19:55,105
And? He's never been heard of since.

324
00:19:55,105 --> 00:19:59,145
They've made enquiries. They've sent
an agent out to visit his property.

325
00:19:59,585 --> 00:20:01,585
There's no sign of him.

326
00:20:03,065 --> 00:20:05,745
I'm sorry. I won't. And that's flat.

327
00:20:06,185 --> 00:20:08,185
Then you'll have to do it, Mr Carson.

328
00:20:08,185 --> 00:20:10,305
I'm not dressing a chauffeur.

329
00:20:10,305 --> 00:20:12,265
He is not a chauffeur now.

330
00:20:12,265 --> 00:20:14,225
Anyway, you don't have to dress him,

331
00:20:14,225 --> 00:20:16,505
just see he's got everything he needs.

332
00:20:16,505 --> 00:20:20,705
I'm not often as one
with Mr Barrow, but no.

333
00:20:20,705 --> 00:20:23,145
Then Alfred must do it. Alfred?

334
00:20:23,145 --> 00:20:26,585
He wouldn't know what to do
beyond collecting dirty shoes.

335
00:20:26,585 --> 00:20:28,585
Well, he'll have to learn.

336
00:20:33,786 --> 00:20:36,266
Is it an Irish tradition?

337
00:20:36,266 --> 00:20:38,506
What? She means not changing.

338
00:20:38,506 --> 00:20:41,426
Of course it isn't,
Granny. It might have been.

339
00:20:41,426 --> 00:20:44,266
You don't change on the
first night of a voyage.

340
00:20:44,266 --> 00:20:46,626
No, my lady, I don't own a set of tails

341
00:20:46,626 --> 00:20:49,946
or a dinner jacket either. I
wouldn't get any use out of them.

342
00:20:49,946 --> 00:20:53,706
Well, I hope you own a morning coat
since you're here for a wedding.

343
00:20:53,706 --> 00:20:57,826
No, I'm afraid I don't. We live
a different kind of life, Papa.

344
00:20:57,826 --> 00:20:59,826
Obviously.

345
00:21:00,066 --> 00:21:02,466
Could you lower it a
bit, please, Mr Carson?

346
00:21:04,466 --> 00:21:07,106
You should buy a Downton
wardrobe and leave it here.

347
00:21:07,106 --> 00:21:10,106
Then you won't have to pack
when you come. What a good idea.

348
00:21:10,106 --> 00:21:13,466
I'm afraid I can't turn into
somebody else just to please you.

349
00:21:13,466 --> 00:21:17,386
More's the pity. Oh, no, why
should you change to please us?

350
00:21:17,386 --> 00:21:19,506
What is the general feeling in Ireland now?

351
00:21:19,506 --> 00:21:24,066
That we're in sight of throwing off the
English yoke. Do you approve of the new act?

352
00:21:24,066 --> 00:21:27,026
Would you of your country being
divided by a foreign power?

353
00:21:27,026 --> 00:21:30,066
Well, won't it bring home rule
for Southern Ireland nearer?

354
00:21:30,066 --> 00:21:32,986
Home rule on English terms
presided over by an English king.

355
00:21:32,986 --> 00:21:34,826
Is keeping the monarchy a problem?

356
00:21:34,826 --> 00:21:38,146
Would it be a problem for you
to be ruled by the German Kaiser?

357
00:21:40,506 --> 00:21:42,546
Carson, are you all right?

358
00:21:42,546 --> 00:21:45,426
I've been very clumsy,
my lord. I do apologise.

359
00:21:45,426 --> 00:21:50,026
Is it true that Irish gardens
have more variety than ours?

360
00:21:50,026 --> 00:21:54,306
Oh, yes. Don't you remember Lady
Dufferin's ball at Claneboye?

361
00:21:54,306 --> 00:21:56,266
The gardens there were heavenly.

362
00:21:58,826 --> 00:22:02,266
I thought them very down on him.
That is because you know nothing.

363
00:22:02,266 --> 00:22:04,186
And wasn't he down on them,

364
00:22:04,186 --> 00:22:07,066
insulting our country, insulting the King?

365
00:22:07,066 --> 00:22:09,906
I thought it was a miracle
his lordship held his temper.

366
00:22:09,906 --> 00:22:12,266
But it must be hard, Mr Carson.

367
00:22:12,266 --> 00:22:16,146
To sit up there with people
he used to drive around.

368
00:22:16,986 --> 00:22:18,986
It is hard, Mrs Hughes.

369
00:22:20,306 --> 00:22:22,346
Please, sit down.

370
00:22:22,346 --> 00:22:24,346
Is there something we can do, sir?

371
00:22:25,746 --> 00:22:27,906
I just wanted to come down to say hello.

372
00:22:27,906 --> 00:22:32,506
I wouldn't want you to think I'd got
too big for my boots. That's nice.

373
00:22:33,426 --> 00:22:35,466
I hope you and Lady Sybil are well?

374
00:22:35,466 --> 00:22:37,466
We are. Thank you.

375
00:22:37,466 --> 00:22:39,866
And we've been following
the story of Mr Bates.

376
00:22:39,866 --> 00:22:41,626
Mary keeps us informed.

377
00:22:44,026 --> 00:22:46,746
Still, I mustn't interrupt your dinner.

378
00:22:47,146 --> 00:22:49,146
Thank you for coming down.

379
00:22:54,986 --> 00:22:56,826
He's settled into his new life.

380
00:22:56,826 --> 00:22:59,106
'Mary keeps us informed.'

381
00:22:59,106 --> 00:23:02,586
Well, he knows her now.
What's that got to do with it?

382
00:23:02,586 --> 00:23:06,266
His lordship would never call her
Mary when talking to me. Never.

383
00:23:07,506 --> 00:23:10,986
If he wants to play their game,
he'd better learn their rules.

384
00:23:12,626 --> 00:23:15,746
Tomorrow let's ask the servants
to come up and dine with us

385
00:23:15,746 --> 00:23:17,706
to make things easier.

386
00:23:17,706 --> 00:23:21,346
You must get him to stop calling
Granny 'my lady'. And Mama.

387
00:23:21,346 --> 00:23:25,146
We need something that doesn't
sound too stiff and grand.

388
00:23:25,146 --> 00:23:27,146
Lady Grantham, of course.

389
00:23:27,626 --> 00:23:29,626
And he can call me Lord Grantham.

390
00:23:30,826 --> 00:23:33,306
That doesn't sound stiff or grand at all.

391
00:23:33,666 --> 00:23:35,666
One step at a time.

392
00:23:40,426 --> 00:23:43,346
So what did the lawyer
want? I presume he turned up.

393
00:23:43,346 --> 00:23:46,066
He did, and it's rather complicated.

394
00:23:46,626 --> 00:23:49,226
But you were right. It
was about Reggie's will.

395
00:23:49,306 --> 00:23:51,426
So he's left you something?

396
00:23:51,426 --> 00:23:54,706
Never mind that now. Sit down
and tell me about the relations

397
00:23:54,706 --> 00:23:58,506
that are coming for the wedding. I
want to unscramble them in my head.

398
00:23:58,826 --> 00:24:02,506
Go to bed when you're done.
I'll go to bed when I'm ready.

399
00:24:03,466 --> 00:24:07,146
What's happened to you? Have you
swapped places with your evil twin?

400
00:24:07,146 --> 00:24:10,586
I'd like to know where the new
maid is. That's what you promised.

401
00:24:10,586 --> 00:24:12,586
They've got a footman. Where's the maid?

402
00:24:12,586 --> 00:24:15,746
I know and I'm sorry, but
I spoke to Mr Carson tonight

403
00:24:15,746 --> 00:24:18,026
and they won't be taking anyone new on.

404
00:24:18,026 --> 00:24:22,026
Except a footman. I don't
know how Mr Carson managed it

405
00:24:22,026 --> 00:24:24,266
because his lordship's put his foot down.

406
00:24:24,266 --> 00:24:28,386
But you're called my assistant now and
you've seven shillings extra every month.

407
00:24:28,386 --> 00:24:31,466
You've still kept me here with
a dishonest representation.

408
00:24:31,466 --> 00:24:34,426
Oh, dear! Have you swallowed a dictionary?

409
00:24:37,666 --> 00:24:40,786
Somehow none of it seems to
matter when we're in Dublin.

410
00:24:41,226 --> 00:24:43,546
Class and all that just seems to fade away.

411
00:24:44,466 --> 00:24:48,346
I'm Mrs Branson and we get on with
our lives like millions of others.

412
00:24:49,026 --> 00:24:51,026
But here he feels so patronised.

413
00:24:51,786 --> 00:24:55,186
And he hates it. But you don't regret it?

414
00:24:55,186 --> 00:24:57,186
No, never.

415
00:24:58,026 --> 00:25:00,026
He's a wonderful, wonderful man.

416
00:25:00,586 --> 00:25:02,426
I just wish you knew him.

417
00:25:02,426 --> 00:25:04,306
Darling, we will know him.

418
00:25:04,306 --> 00:25:06,506
We'll know him and value him. I promise.

419
00:25:08,226 --> 00:25:10,226
Anyway...

420
00:25:11,106 --> 00:25:14,866
I'd best go upstairs and make
sure he's not too suicidal.

421
00:25:15,226 --> 00:25:17,226
Good night.

422
00:25:17,506 --> 00:25:20,306
Oh, by the way, I don't
know if Mama's told you...

423
00:25:20,306 --> 00:25:23,226
But the whole Grey family's
coming tomorrow night.

424
00:25:24,466 --> 00:25:26,466
Including Larry?

425
00:25:27,106 --> 00:25:29,106
Crikey. You'd better warn Tom.

426
00:25:30,106 --> 00:25:34,306
Oh, and, Sybil, I wouldn't tell
Papa about being Mrs Branson.

427
00:25:39,906 --> 00:25:41,746
But who are the Greys?

428
00:25:41,746 --> 00:25:43,906
And why does it matter that they're coming?

429
00:25:43,906 --> 00:25:46,266
The father, Lord Merton,
is Mary's godfather.

430
00:25:46,266 --> 00:25:49,586
But Larry Grey used to be
keen on me, when we were young.

431
00:25:49,586 --> 00:25:51,626
Were you keen on him?

432
00:25:51,626 --> 00:25:53,626
No. I don't think so.

433
00:25:54,426 --> 00:25:56,426
I can hardly remember, to be honest.

434
00:25:56,706 --> 00:26:00,706
So what are you saying?
Nothing particularly.

435
00:26:01,426 --> 00:26:04,506
But we could run into
Ripon and find some tails.

436
00:26:04,506 --> 00:26:06,506
We have the money.

437
00:26:06,506 --> 00:26:08,506
I won't spend more of that money.

438
00:26:09,626 --> 00:26:11,626
All right.

439
00:26:12,466 --> 00:26:14,986
Please don't talk about
Ireland all the time.

440
00:26:15,426 --> 00:26:17,706
I just want to make things easier for you.

441
00:26:19,306 --> 00:26:21,306
For me or for you?

442
00:26:21,666 --> 00:26:23,666
Don't disappoint me, Sybil.

443
00:26:23,986 --> 00:26:25,986
Not now that we're here.

444
00:26:35,386 --> 00:26:37,266
Shall I order the car?

445
00:26:37,266 --> 00:26:39,386
I don't think I can
refuse a lift with Mother

446
00:26:39,386 --> 00:26:41,666
and then make the poor man go out again.

447
00:26:41,666 --> 00:26:43,666
I'll walk. It might rain.

448
00:26:44,306 --> 00:26:46,106
Then I'll get wet.

449
00:26:47,426 --> 00:26:49,426
Now come and kiss me.

450
00:26:53,146 --> 00:26:57,506
So, if they can't find Mr...Pillbox,
what will you do with the money?

451
00:26:57,506 --> 00:27:00,266
Pullbrook. And they will find him.

452
00:27:01,066 --> 00:27:03,266
But if they don't?

453
00:27:03,906 --> 00:27:06,106
Then I'll decide what to do.

454
00:27:06,826 --> 00:27:08,826
Or we will.

455
00:27:11,746 --> 00:27:15,586
Because I can't keep it. No, of course not.

456
00:27:19,106 --> 00:27:23,026
Why have you so heavily invested in
one enterprise? Wasn't it foolish?

457
00:27:23,426 --> 00:27:26,266
Has some of my fortune been lost?

458
00:27:27,746 --> 00:27:29,746
Some.

459
00:27:31,266 --> 00:27:33,186
All.

460
00:27:33,186 --> 00:27:35,186
Almost all.

461
00:27:42,906 --> 00:27:44,906
Oh, my dear.

462
00:27:50,626 --> 00:27:52,626
How terrible for you.

463
00:27:53,466 --> 00:27:55,586
It's not so good for you.

464
00:27:55,586 --> 00:27:59,066
Don't worry about me. I'm an
American. Have gun, will travel.

465
00:28:01,426 --> 00:28:03,786
Thank god for you, anyway.

466
00:28:07,906 --> 00:28:09,906
You know what?

467
00:28:10,586 --> 00:28:12,786
I'm glad we have a wedding to celebrate.

468
00:28:14,586 --> 00:28:16,586
Let's make sure it's a great day.

469
00:28:20,066 --> 00:28:23,066
If it's to be our last, let's
make it a wonderful last.

470
00:28:25,346 --> 00:28:29,066
Enjoy our lovely home and the lovely
people we spend our life among.

471
00:28:42,906 --> 00:28:44,986
Bit early for drowning your sorrows.

472
00:28:44,986 --> 00:28:47,906
I thought it might be better
if I moved down to the pub.

473
00:28:48,546 --> 00:28:52,586
You're not serious? I can't go through
many more dinners like last night.

474
00:28:52,586 --> 00:28:54,586
You don't make it easy for them.

475
00:28:54,946 --> 00:28:58,466
Do you really think you can
recruit cousin Robert for Sinn Fein?

476
00:28:58,586 --> 00:29:00,626
I don't know what gets into me.

477
00:29:00,626 --> 00:29:03,506
I can see them staring and I
know they don't want me here.

478
00:29:03,506 --> 00:29:05,346
Well, don't include me. Or Mary.

479
00:29:05,346 --> 00:29:08,946
She wasn't too keen on the idea of
a chauffeur for a brother-in-law.

480
00:29:08,946 --> 00:29:11,066
Forget that. She's a pragmatist.

481
00:29:11,306 --> 00:29:14,666
She could be a tough fighter,
too. Let's hope she's not tested.

482
00:29:14,666 --> 00:29:18,946
Forget this and walk back. We're
brothers-in-law with high-minded wives.

483
00:29:18,946 --> 00:29:20,946
We'd better stick together.

484
00:29:27,986 --> 00:29:30,026
It's all there.

485
00:29:30,026 --> 00:29:32,746
Friends - though there
weren't too many -

486
00:29:32,746 --> 00:29:34,826
tradesmen, acquaintances.

487
00:29:34,826 --> 00:29:37,346
But I can't see what
you'll get out of them.

488
00:29:37,346 --> 00:29:40,026
I do not believe, when Vera
decided to kill herself,

489
00:29:40,026 --> 00:29:42,586
she never mentioned it
to another living soul.

490
00:29:42,586 --> 00:29:44,346
We know she left no note.

491
00:29:44,346 --> 00:29:46,346
I wish to god she had.

492
00:29:46,986 --> 00:29:50,026
But why are you sure it
was suicide and not murder?

493
00:29:50,026 --> 00:29:52,186
Well, I know you didn't kill her.

494
00:29:52,186 --> 00:29:54,426
What's the alternative?

495
00:29:54,426 --> 00:29:58,186
A thief broke in, cooked an arsenic
pie and forced her to eat it?

496
00:29:58,586 --> 00:30:00,866
It's not a very likely scenario.

497
00:30:01,946 --> 00:30:03,946
You can see why they convicted me.

498
00:30:04,346 --> 00:30:06,706
I'm going to write to everyone in the book,

499
00:30:06,706 --> 00:30:10,066
in case she said, or,
please god, wrote anything

500
00:30:10,066 --> 00:30:12,066
that could suggest a desire to die.

501
00:30:12,746 --> 00:30:15,186
How long will that take?

502
00:30:15,186 --> 00:30:18,546
Why? Are you going somewhere?

503
00:30:21,226 --> 00:30:25,106
I should have gone into cooking.
I could pick it up in a trice.

504
00:30:25,106 --> 00:30:28,026
Why didn't you, then? It's
a hard ladder for a man.

505
00:30:28,506 --> 00:30:32,146
For every Escoffier and Monsieur
Careme there's a thousand dogsbodies

506
00:30:32,146 --> 00:30:34,866
taking orders from a
cross, red-faced old woman.

507
00:30:34,866 --> 00:30:36,626
Who's this you're discussing?

508
00:30:36,626 --> 00:30:39,626
Hello, Mrs Patmore. I didn't
see you standing there.

509
00:30:39,626 --> 00:30:41,626
Obviously not.

510
00:30:42,026 --> 00:30:46,106
Sarah thought I'd be better off as a
butler and that's what I'm trying for.

511
00:30:46,106 --> 00:30:48,866
I think you're right. I'd
rather be giving the orders.

512
00:30:48,866 --> 00:30:52,546
To a cross and red-faced
old woman. Yes, we know.

513
00:30:56,946 --> 00:30:59,426
There. Is that what you meant?

514
00:30:59,426 --> 00:31:01,426
Yes. Perfect.

515
00:31:02,146 --> 00:31:04,146
Slightly new, but not too different.

516
00:31:05,706 --> 00:31:07,906
We'll see if Sir Anthony notices.

517
00:31:11,026 --> 00:31:14,146
I know they all think he's
too old for me, but he's not.

518
00:31:14,346 --> 00:31:17,226
Bates is older than you and
you're as happy as lovebirds.

519
00:31:17,986 --> 00:31:19,986
Our situation is hardly ideal,

520
00:31:21,306 --> 00:31:23,826
but, yes, we're very happy together.

521
00:31:24,666 --> 00:31:26,666
Which is all that matters.

522
00:31:27,186 --> 00:31:29,186
As I keep telling them.

523
00:31:34,106 --> 00:31:37,666
I've no time to talk. His
lordship's not come up yet.

524
00:31:38,106 --> 00:31:40,106
Well? What is it?

525
00:31:40,906 --> 00:31:44,786
I was hoping you could help young
Alfred to find his way about.

526
00:31:46,026 --> 00:31:48,626
As a footman, you mean. As a valet.

527
00:31:49,906 --> 00:31:51,946
He's looking after Mr Branson now.

528
00:31:51,946 --> 00:31:54,826
Though I daresay a
chauffeur can dress himself.

529
00:31:54,826 --> 00:31:58,146
But you could tell him what he
needs to know, give him an advantage.

530
00:31:58,146 --> 00:31:59,986
Why? What's the rush?

531
00:31:59,986 --> 00:32:02,906
You've heard Mr Matthew
has turned down Mr Molesley?

532
00:32:03,426 --> 00:32:05,426
Blimey, you don't want much, do you?

533
00:32:06,746 --> 00:32:09,386
Can you remember what I had
to go through to be a valet?

534
00:32:09,386 --> 00:32:11,786
Of course. I watched it, didn't I?

535
00:32:11,786 --> 00:32:14,786
But young Alfred is to make
the great leap in one bound?

536
00:32:14,786 --> 00:32:17,906
Well, I'm sorry, Miss
O'Brien, but I'm not convinced.

537
00:32:18,946 --> 00:32:20,946
If you'll excuse me.

538
00:32:44,515 --> 00:32:46,835
It's infuriating.
There's nothing he can do.

539
00:32:46,835 --> 00:32:48,875
I don't agree. I think it's feeble.

540
00:32:48,875 --> 00:32:52,875
He should will himself not to be
ill and then collapse the next day.

541
00:32:52,875 --> 00:32:56,555
Whom will you ask instead? I'm not sure.

542
00:32:56,955 --> 00:32:58,795
I've known Sybil all my life.

543
00:32:58,795 --> 00:33:02,595
You can imagine how curious I was
when I found out you'd be here tonight.

544
00:33:02,595 --> 00:33:04,955
Never thought we'd meet in person.

545
00:33:04,955 --> 00:33:07,355
As opposed to what? In spirit?

546
00:33:09,395 --> 00:33:12,675
Well, you see, to us, in marrying you

547
00:33:12,675 --> 00:33:15,715
it seemed like Sybil had
left Downton Abbey forever.

548
00:33:17,235 --> 00:33:19,235
If you know what I mean.

549
00:33:19,915 --> 00:33:21,915
I know exactly what you mean.

550
00:33:23,675 --> 00:33:27,995
Did they lose your suitcase on the
way over? How maddening for you.

551
00:33:27,995 --> 00:33:30,795
No, my suitcase arrived safely, thank you.

552
00:33:30,795 --> 00:33:32,795
Along with my manners.

553
00:33:37,955 --> 00:33:41,155
He's still dressed as the man
from the Prudential, I see.

554
00:33:42,035 --> 00:33:45,355
Yes, it's nice to have someone
from the real world, isn't it?

555
00:33:48,715 --> 00:33:51,635
Hello, Mama. Can I tempt you
to one of these new cocktails?

556
00:33:51,635 --> 00:33:53,595
I don't think so.

557
00:33:53,595 --> 00:33:56,435
They look too exciting for
so early in the evening.

558
00:33:56,435 --> 00:33:58,555
Don't you think so, Carson?

559
00:33:58,555 --> 00:34:01,075
Better avoided, my lady. I think so.

560
00:34:02,515 --> 00:34:05,915
What a pleasure it is to see
you out and about, Sir Anthony.

561
00:34:06,435 --> 00:34:10,315
I want to say, 'Can I be of any
help?' but you don't seem to need any.

562
00:34:10,315 --> 00:34:13,835
He doesn't need help at all, do
you? He won't let me do anything.

563
00:34:13,835 --> 00:34:15,635
Mustn't be a nuisance, you know.

564
00:34:16,355 --> 00:34:18,835
Are you coming to the wedding? Of course.

565
00:34:20,275 --> 00:34:22,275
Well, if you really want me.

566
00:34:22,915 --> 00:34:25,235
I do. I really do.

567
00:34:26,915 --> 00:34:30,835
You look very nice. Have you done
something jolly with your hair?

568
00:34:32,155 --> 00:34:33,995
I say. What the devil...

569
00:34:33,995 --> 00:34:35,555
What is it?

570
00:34:35,555 --> 00:34:37,555
Dinner is served, your ladyship.

571
00:34:41,275 --> 00:34:43,075
How's it going? Awkward.

572
00:34:43,075 --> 00:34:46,715
Mr Branson's well away and
Lady Sybil doesn't like it much.

573
00:34:46,715 --> 00:34:48,835
He's only had one cocktail.

574
00:34:48,835 --> 00:34:52,235
Maybe he was drinking before
he came down to calm his nerves.

575
00:34:54,595 --> 00:34:57,475
No, I don't agree, and I
don't care who knows it.

576
00:34:57,475 --> 00:35:00,355
The Black and Tans are there
to restore order, are they?

577
00:35:00,355 --> 00:35:02,755
Why don't they just murder
the entire population

578
00:35:02,755 --> 00:35:04,955
and then you wouldn't
hear a squeak from them.

579
00:35:04,955 --> 00:35:08,875
Is there any way to shut him up? If I
knew that, he wouldn't be here at all.

580
00:35:08,875 --> 00:35:11,395
Are you interested in
Irish politics, Lord Merton?

581
00:35:11,395 --> 00:35:14,475
I was only just saying... He's
interested in Irish repression.

582
00:35:14,475 --> 00:35:18,275
Like all of you. Look, of
course this stuff matters to you.

583
00:35:18,275 --> 00:35:20,115
Yes, it does matter...

584
00:35:20,115 --> 00:35:23,715
..this stuff. It matters a very great deal.

585
00:35:23,715 --> 00:35:25,955
What's so funny? Nothing.

586
00:35:25,955 --> 00:35:29,155
I'm just enjoying this vivid
display of Irish character.

587
00:35:30,195 --> 00:35:33,115
Please, Tom. We don't
need to wear everyone out.

588
00:35:33,355 --> 00:35:39,035
Why? What's the matter? Am
I not being polite enough?

589
00:35:39,675 --> 00:35:42,275
What a minute. This was
down to you, wasn't it?

590
00:35:42,275 --> 00:35:44,635
I don't know what you mean. Yes, you do.

591
00:35:44,635 --> 00:35:48,555
You put something in his drink,
didn't you? Just before we came in.

592
00:35:49,435 --> 00:35:52,555
That's not true, is it, Larry?
What a beastly thing to do.

593
00:35:52,555 --> 00:35:56,075
Oh, come on, Edith. That's not like
you. You could always take a joke.

594
00:35:56,075 --> 00:35:58,075
A bully's defence.

595
00:35:58,075 --> 00:36:02,595
Listen, Mr Grey has given Mr Branson
something to make him appear drunk.

596
00:36:02,595 --> 00:36:05,835
Could it be drink? No, not
drink. Some horrible pill.

597
00:36:05,835 --> 00:36:08,635
Sybil, take him upstairs.
Il ne manque que ca.

598
00:36:09,275 --> 00:36:11,355
Tom has been the victim of a cruel prank

599
00:36:11,355 --> 00:36:14,315
which I know you'll all
be kind enough to forget.

600
00:36:14,315 --> 00:36:18,915
Forgive, perhaps. Forget?
Never. Is this true, Larry?

601
00:36:18,915 --> 00:36:22,035
I don't know why you're
getting so hot under the collar.

602
00:36:22,035 --> 00:36:23,995
He's only a grubby little chauffeur.

603
00:36:23,995 --> 00:36:25,955
Be silent this instant, sir!

604
00:36:28,675 --> 00:36:31,515
I apologise for my son,
Mr Branson. Unreservedly.

605
00:36:32,595 --> 00:36:35,195
I only hope you'll
recover before the wedding.

606
00:36:36,315 --> 00:36:38,235
I hope so too.

607
00:36:38,235 --> 00:36:40,635
Since I want him to be my best man.

608
00:36:44,275 --> 00:36:46,915
Bravo. Well said.

609
00:36:46,915 --> 00:36:49,035
Do you really mean it? Honestly?

610
00:36:49,035 --> 00:36:52,235
I've told you. If we're mad enough
to take on the Crawley girls,

611
00:36:52,235 --> 00:36:54,235
we have to stick together.

612
00:36:54,795 --> 00:36:56,915
Thank you, Matthew. Thank you so much.

613
00:36:59,915 --> 00:37:03,635
That was rather marvellous of you
to expose Larry Grey like that.

614
00:37:03,635 --> 00:37:07,035
You saved the day. I wouldn't
say that. Matthew saved the day.

615
00:37:07,035 --> 00:37:09,035
No, it was you.

616
00:37:09,995 --> 00:37:13,715
I do hope we'll see a bit more
of you once the wedding's over.

617
00:37:13,715 --> 00:37:15,795
Well... Wouldn't you like that?

618
00:37:15,795 --> 00:37:17,795
I should like that very much.

619
00:37:18,595 --> 00:37:20,515
Much more than I probably ought to.

620
00:37:21,155 --> 00:37:23,275
Edith, let Sir Anthony go.

621
00:37:32,515 --> 00:37:34,515
Goodnight, Papa.

622
00:37:42,035 --> 00:37:43,995
Well, that's the last of them.

623
00:37:43,995 --> 00:37:46,315
Where are the others? They've gone to bed.

624
00:37:46,315 --> 00:37:48,315
So's Edith. And so should we.

625
00:37:49,835 --> 00:37:53,555
Golly. What a night for
the county to feed off.

626
00:37:54,115 --> 00:37:56,915
It was good of Matthew to show solidarity.

627
00:37:57,395 --> 00:37:59,395
I suppose so.

628
00:37:59,835 --> 00:38:02,595
We're going to need all the
solidarity we can muster.

629
00:38:02,595 --> 00:38:04,595
When will you tell the girls?

630
00:38:07,275 --> 00:38:10,955
I think I should tell Mary now.
Not before the wedding, surely.

631
00:38:11,395 --> 00:38:14,515
I must. They're disagreeing
about where they should live.

632
00:38:14,515 --> 00:38:16,835
It would be wrong for
me to keep it from them.

633
00:38:16,835 --> 00:38:20,115
They can discuss it on the
honeymoon and decide more sensibly.

634
00:38:21,635 --> 00:38:26,275
Should we say something to your
mother when she gets here? No.

635
00:38:26,275 --> 00:38:30,395
She'll go into state mourning and
cast a pall over the whole proceedings.

636
00:38:31,075 --> 00:38:34,555
Thank god she missed tonight's drama
or we'd never hear the end of it.

637
00:38:34,555 --> 00:38:38,155
Don't worry. She'll bring
enough drama of her own.

638
00:38:38,835 --> 00:38:40,835
Hm.

639
00:38:44,635 --> 00:38:46,675
It won't work, you know.

640
00:38:46,675 --> 00:38:50,195
If you don't admit your
guilt, they won't let you go.

641
00:38:50,195 --> 00:38:52,355
How can I admit what isn't true?

642
00:38:53,515 --> 00:38:56,555
Why do you have to be so pious?

643
00:38:58,915 --> 00:39:00,915
You're a touchy fella, aren't you?

644
00:39:02,675 --> 00:39:05,195
Don't push me, Craig.

645
00:39:05,195 --> 00:39:07,195
Is that a warning?

646
00:39:07,555 --> 00:39:10,195
Yes. Yes, it is.

647
00:39:13,275 --> 00:39:15,275
I'm warning you.

648
00:39:22,635 --> 00:39:24,715
I'm not sure about the hat.

649
00:39:24,715 --> 00:39:26,875
Is it supposed to look crooked?

650
00:39:26,875 --> 00:39:30,475
Don't listen to her. I love it.
You're not to change a thing.

651
00:39:30,475 --> 00:39:33,275
Anna? I think you look lovely, my lady.

652
00:39:33,275 --> 00:39:35,075
(KNOCK ON THE DOOR)

653
00:39:35,075 --> 00:39:37,715
Stop. Wait. Who is it?

654
00:39:37,715 --> 00:39:40,995
Your long-suffering papa.
I suppose he can come in.

655
00:39:43,675 --> 00:39:46,035
What's this for? Going away.

656
00:39:46,395 --> 00:39:48,955
How does it look? Expensive.

657
00:39:49,635 --> 00:39:51,635
Twice the national debt, I'm afraid.

658
00:39:51,635 --> 00:39:53,915
(CHUCKLES) But I know you don't mind.

659
00:39:54,915 --> 00:39:57,875
Can I have one moment alone
to give Mary my blessing?

660
00:39:57,875 --> 00:40:01,475
That's lovely. Shoo, everyone.

661
00:40:07,475 --> 00:40:09,475
Go on, bless me.

662
00:40:10,195 --> 00:40:14,755
Of course. But there's something
I feel I ought to tell you first.

663
00:40:15,595 --> 00:40:19,355
I wanted to wait until you got
back, but I don't believe I can.

664
00:40:20,195 --> 00:40:22,395
That sounds rather ominous.

665
00:40:27,395 --> 00:40:30,235
Hello, Mr Molesley. I got a
message to call on Mrs Crawley.

666
00:40:30,235 --> 00:40:34,555
Very good, sir. If you'd like to
give me your hat and coat, sir.

667
00:40:35,035 --> 00:40:38,875
Are you going up to the house
to welcome the Queen of Sheba?

668
00:40:38,875 --> 00:40:40,875
Oh, I think so.

669
00:40:40,875 --> 00:40:42,915
Are you? No.

670
00:40:42,915 --> 00:40:44,875
I'll pay homage at dinner.

671
00:40:44,875 --> 00:40:47,915
I've always admired the way
Mrs Levinson is never overawed

672
00:40:47,915 --> 00:40:53,275
by the set-up at Downton. Was
Napoleon overawed by the Bourbons?

673
00:40:54,715 --> 00:40:56,715
Come in, Tom.

674
00:40:58,315 --> 00:41:00,835
May I call you Tom? Of course.

675
00:41:01,835 --> 00:41:04,635
Good afternoon, my lady.
That is, Lady Grantham.

676
00:41:04,995 --> 00:41:06,995
I'm glad to find you here because...

677
00:41:07,915 --> 00:41:09,995
I want to apologise for last night.

678
00:41:10,595 --> 00:41:13,475
Oh, there's no need. We
know it was not your fault.

679
00:41:13,475 --> 00:41:17,715
You weren't the first drunk in
that dining room, I can assure you.

680
00:41:18,355 --> 00:41:20,395
Only the first republican.

681
00:41:20,395 --> 00:41:22,155
Well, you've got me there.

682
00:41:23,235 --> 00:41:25,275
Why was it you wanted to see me?

683
00:41:25,275 --> 00:41:28,075
We asked Molesley to look out
Matthew's old morning coat.

684
00:41:28,075 --> 00:41:30,115
He's confident he can make it fit.

685
00:41:30,115 --> 00:41:31,955
That's very kind, ladies.

686
00:41:31,955 --> 00:41:34,555
But I don't approve of these costumes.

687
00:41:34,555 --> 00:41:36,675
I see them as the uniform of oppression

688
00:41:36,675 --> 00:41:38,915
and I should be uncomfortable wearing them.

689
00:41:38,915 --> 00:41:40,915
Have you quite finished?

690
00:41:41,675 --> 00:41:43,675
I have. Good.

691
00:41:44,435 --> 00:41:46,635
Please take off your coat.

692
00:41:47,795 --> 00:41:49,635
Molesley, do help him.

693
00:41:49,635 --> 00:41:51,635
If you'll just slip it off, sir.

694
00:41:56,435 --> 00:41:59,035
Shouldn't he put the waistcoat on first?

695
00:41:59,035 --> 00:42:02,755
What's going on? They're
forcing me into a morning coat.

696
00:42:02,755 --> 00:42:06,955
He has no say in it? No,
he doesn't. And nor do you.

697
00:42:07,635 --> 00:42:10,115
Well, what do you think, Molesley?

698
00:42:10,115 --> 00:42:13,075
It'll need lifting a little here, my lady.

699
00:42:13,435 --> 00:42:15,315
I'll move the buttons. Fine.

700
00:42:15,315 --> 00:42:17,955
I think the shoulders look odd.

701
00:42:17,955 --> 00:42:19,955
Mm.

702
00:42:43,755 --> 00:42:46,595
Come war and peace, Downton still stands

703
00:42:46,595 --> 00:42:48,595
and the Crawleys are still in it.

704
00:42:50,075 --> 00:42:52,155
Cora. Mother, how lovely to see you.

705
00:42:52,155 --> 00:42:54,155
As long as it is.

706
00:42:54,155 --> 00:42:57,435
Robert, aren't you going to kiss
me? With the greatest enthusiasm.

707
00:42:58,755 --> 00:43:00,675
Tell me, where does this come from?

708
00:43:01,235 --> 00:43:03,235
I hired it in Liverpool. Why?

709
00:43:03,235 --> 00:43:05,995
I thought it might be a
gift from the US government

710
00:43:05,995 --> 00:43:08,035
to help get Britain back on its feet.

711
00:43:08,915 --> 00:43:13,275
Carson and Mrs Hughes. The world
has moved on since last we met.

712
00:43:13,275 --> 00:43:15,795
And we have moved on with it, madam.

713
00:43:15,795 --> 00:43:17,635
Really?

714
00:43:17,635 --> 00:43:21,035
It seems so strange to think
of the English embracing change.

715
00:43:21,035 --> 00:43:23,115
Mrs Hughes, this is my maid
- Reed.

716
00:43:23,515 --> 00:43:26,755
Sybil, tell me all about the
arrangements for the birth.

717
00:43:26,755 --> 00:43:29,875
We do these things so
much better in the States.

718
00:43:30,355 --> 00:43:32,795
Edith, still no-one special?

719
00:43:33,435 --> 00:43:37,915
Oh, well, never mind. You must take
a tip from the modern American girl.

720
00:43:37,915 --> 00:43:40,555
Mary, dearest Mary.

721
00:43:40,555 --> 00:43:43,795
Now, you tell me all of your wedding plans

722
00:43:43,795 --> 00:43:46,075
and I'll see what I can do to improve them.

723
00:43:56,755 --> 00:44:01,115
What's the matter with
you? Mrs Patmore knows.

724
00:44:01,115 --> 00:44:04,355
Shall I tell you Mrs Levinson's
requirements during her stay?

725
00:44:04,355 --> 00:44:08,115
No, tell her. Er, yes,
Miss Reed. How can I help?

726
00:44:08,435 --> 00:44:11,355
To start with I will need
goats' milk in the mornings.

727
00:44:11,355 --> 00:44:13,355
Goats' milk? Fancy that.

728
00:44:13,555 --> 00:44:15,355
She drinks only boiled water.

729
00:44:15,355 --> 00:44:17,715
Really? In England, that is.

730
00:44:17,715 --> 00:44:20,355
Shouldn't Daisy do this?
I ought to take the tea up.

731
00:44:20,355 --> 00:44:22,355
I'll have it ready in a moment.

732
00:44:25,115 --> 00:44:28,475
No fats, no crab and nothing
from the marrow family.

733
00:44:29,355 --> 00:44:32,035
Do explain again how exactly

734
00:44:32,035 --> 00:44:34,555
you are related to all of us, Mr Crawley.

735
00:44:35,595 --> 00:44:37,755
Rather distantly, I'm afraid.

736
00:44:37,755 --> 00:44:42,555
My great-great-grandfather was
a younger son of a third earl.

737
00:44:42,555 --> 00:44:46,955
My. I'm going to have to write
that down, so I can study it.

738
00:44:46,955 --> 00:44:50,155
Look at our page in Burke's.
You'll find Matthew there.

739
00:44:50,155 --> 00:44:52,395
Good. Because I would so like to understand

740
00:44:52,395 --> 00:44:55,595
why he gets to inherit
my late husband's money.

741
00:44:56,275 --> 00:44:58,475
I know. It's funny, isn't it?

742
00:44:59,235 --> 00:45:01,395
Not everyone shares your sense of humour.

743
00:45:01,395 --> 00:45:04,315
Surely it doesn't matter now
that they're getting married.

744
00:45:04,315 --> 00:45:07,635
In fact, we'd better turn him out
or it'll be bad luck for tomorrow.

745
00:45:07,635 --> 00:45:09,635
CORA: Quite right.

746
00:45:16,195 --> 00:45:18,915
You must be the chauffeur
I've heard so much about.

747
00:45:18,915 --> 00:45:22,395
I am, ma'am. Tom's a
journalist now, Grandmama.

748
00:45:22,395 --> 00:45:26,235
Oh, well, well. I've heard of those
journeys on my side of the water.

749
00:45:26,835 --> 00:45:29,915
It's very pleasant to hear
of them happening here.

750
00:45:33,075 --> 00:45:36,115
It's all right, Mama. You
can leave us unchaperoned.

751
00:45:36,475 --> 00:45:38,755
After tomorrow, all things are permitted.

752
00:45:38,755 --> 00:45:40,835
Don't embarrass me.

753
00:45:40,835 --> 00:45:42,835
Bye, Matthew.

754
00:45:42,835 --> 00:45:45,195
Get a good night's sleep.

755
00:45:49,835 --> 00:45:52,995
How many moments of Crawley
history has this room seen?

756
00:45:53,635 --> 00:45:55,675
And many more to come.

757
00:45:56,395 --> 00:45:58,395
I hope so.

758
00:45:59,355 --> 00:46:03,195
In fact, what happened in
the search for...Mr Pumpkin?

759
00:46:03,795 --> 00:46:06,195
Swire's heir. Have you heard anything?

760
00:46:06,195 --> 00:46:09,395
Yes, Charkham sent a telegram.
I've got it here, actually.

761
00:46:16,755 --> 00:46:19,875
'Convincing proof of
Pullbrook's death. Stop.

762
00:46:20,475 --> 00:46:22,515
Investigating date.'

763
00:46:23,275 --> 00:46:24,995
What does that mean?

764
00:46:24,995 --> 00:46:29,195
Well, if Pullbrook died after
Reggie then his heirs get the money.

765
00:46:29,195 --> 00:46:31,275
If he died first, then I do.

766
00:46:31,275 --> 00:46:34,635
But that's absurd. What right
have his heirs to inherit anything?

767
00:46:34,635 --> 00:46:37,995
Darling, what right have I? Frankly,
what difference does it make?

768
00:46:37,995 --> 00:46:39,835
I shan't keep it if I get it.

769
00:46:39,835 --> 00:46:42,235
Well, actually, you will.

770
00:46:42,915 --> 00:46:45,555
Because something rather
terrible has happened.

771
00:46:46,915 --> 00:46:51,875
You see, apparently Papa has
lost a great deal of money.

772
00:46:53,275 --> 00:46:55,195
Enough to ruin him.

773
00:46:55,195 --> 00:46:57,155
Enough for us to lose Downton.

774
00:46:57,155 --> 00:46:59,195
God, I'm sorry.

775
00:47:00,275 --> 00:47:05,115
I'm so sorry. Yes, but surely if
Mr Pullbrook did die before Swire,

776
00:47:05,115 --> 00:47:07,155
then we're saved.

777
00:47:08,915 --> 00:47:11,155
Darling, I don't think you understand.

778
00:47:12,915 --> 00:47:15,435
Reggie Swire put me in his
will because he believed

779
00:47:15,435 --> 00:47:17,475
I was his daughter's one true love.

780
00:47:18,275 --> 00:47:20,275
So you were. Yes, but...

781
00:47:21,915 --> 00:47:25,275
But I broke Lavinia's heart and
she died. He never knew that.

782
00:47:26,035 --> 00:47:29,595
How could I possibly allow myself
to profit from her death to...

783
00:47:30,395 --> 00:47:32,355
to dine in splendour

784
00:47:32,355 --> 00:47:34,635
because I took away a woman's will to live?

785
00:47:34,635 --> 00:47:38,355
So, you're prepared to destroy us
in payment for your destroying her?

786
00:47:38,355 --> 00:47:42,115
Darling, please. You know I
would do anything for this family.

787
00:47:42,115 --> 00:47:43,995
Anything except help us.

788
00:47:43,995 --> 00:47:48,115
Except save Papa from living out
his days in humiliation and grief.

789
00:47:48,115 --> 00:47:51,115
And what about us? What about our children?

790
00:47:51,115 --> 00:47:53,515
God, Matthew, how can
you be so disappointing?

791
00:47:53,515 --> 00:47:56,355
Mary, please. No! Don't
you see what this means?

792
00:47:56,355 --> 00:47:58,755
Don't you see what a difference this makes?

793
00:47:58,755 --> 00:48:01,475
It means that you're
not on our side, Matthew.

794
00:48:01,475 --> 00:48:04,115
It means that deep down
you're not on our side!

795
00:48:24,276 --> 00:48:26,876
How are you getting on
with your new companion?

796
00:48:26,876 --> 00:48:29,956
I don't like him, but so
far I've kept it to myself.

797
00:48:31,436 --> 00:48:34,156
So, who are the bridesmaids?

798
00:48:35,156 --> 00:48:37,756
You don't care about
all that? You're wrong.

799
00:48:37,756 --> 00:48:39,836
It's the stuff of my dreams.

800
00:48:40,156 --> 00:48:43,236
The panic that a dinner won't be
ready, or a frock isn't ironed,

801
00:48:43,236 --> 00:48:45,236
or a gun wasn't cleaned.

802
00:48:45,316 --> 00:48:47,756
Do you know where you're
going for the honeymoon?

803
00:48:47,756 --> 00:48:49,716
I want to talk about that.

804
00:48:49,716 --> 00:48:52,916
They'll stay in London with Lady
Rosamund for a couple of days,

805
00:48:52,916 --> 00:48:54,916
just to get used to each other...

806
00:48:55,636 --> 00:48:57,756
and then they go to the South of France.

807
00:48:58,356 --> 00:49:02,396
I'll hire replacements in London
and then I'll come home instead.

808
00:49:03,316 --> 00:49:05,356
Lady Mary won't mind. I'll pay.

809
00:49:05,356 --> 00:49:07,436
Why would you do that?

810
00:49:07,436 --> 00:49:09,596
Well, to be near you, of course.

811
00:49:09,596 --> 00:49:11,636
Don't you understand?

812
00:49:11,636 --> 00:49:14,876
While I'm in here you have to
live my life as well as your own.

813
00:49:14,876 --> 00:49:19,676
Go to France, see some
sites, get us some memories.

814
00:49:20,116 --> 00:49:21,916
But I wouldn't be home for a month.

815
00:49:21,916 --> 00:49:24,076
Won't we have something to talk about?

816
00:49:24,076 --> 00:49:26,076
Go. I insist.

817
00:49:27,476 --> 00:49:29,476
For my sake.

818
00:49:30,836 --> 00:49:32,836
I was so afraid I was going to be late.

819
00:49:33,156 --> 00:49:35,156
Ah ha ha.

820
00:49:35,876 --> 00:49:37,876
Violet.

821
00:49:41,156 --> 00:49:42,996
Oh, dear.

822
00:49:42,996 --> 00:49:46,276
I'm afraid the war has
made old women of us both.

823
00:49:46,276 --> 00:49:50,756
Oh, I wouldn't say that. But
then, I always keep out of the sun.

824
00:49:51,636 --> 00:49:53,836
How do you find Downton on your return?

825
00:49:53,836 --> 00:49:55,676
Much the same, really.

826
00:49:55,676 --> 00:49:58,676
Probably too much the same,
but I don't want to cast a pall

827
00:49:58,676 --> 00:50:02,196
over all the happiness.
How could you ever do that?

828
00:50:03,356 --> 00:50:06,036
Tell me, what do you
think of young Lochinvar

829
00:50:06,036 --> 00:50:09,716
who has so ably carried off
our granddaughter and our money?

830
00:50:09,716 --> 00:50:12,436
Do you approve of him?
Not as much as you will...

831
00:50:12,436 --> 00:50:14,636
..when you get to know him.

832
00:50:14,636 --> 00:50:18,596
Has he gone home to change? Oh,
no, we won't see him again tonight.

833
00:50:19,516 --> 00:50:23,276
The groom never sees the bride
the night before the wedding.

834
00:50:24,836 --> 00:50:27,356
Nothing ever alters
for you people, does it?

835
00:50:27,356 --> 00:50:30,276
Revolutions erupt and
monarchies crash to the ground

836
00:50:30,276 --> 00:50:33,196
and the groom still cannot see
the bride before the wedding.

837
00:50:33,636 --> 00:50:38,396
You Americans never understand
the importance of tradition.

838
00:50:39,036 --> 00:50:41,916
Yes, we do. We just don't
give it power over us.

839
00:50:42,476 --> 00:50:45,636
History and tradition took
Europe into a world war.

840
00:50:46,196 --> 00:50:48,956
Maybe you should think
about letting go of its hand.

841
00:50:54,316 --> 00:50:56,276
There you are.

842
00:50:56,276 --> 00:50:58,596
I see you've said hello to Grandmama.

843
00:50:58,596 --> 00:51:00,716
She is like a homing pigeon.

844
00:51:02,396 --> 00:51:05,436
She finds our underbelly every time.

845
00:51:06,796 --> 00:51:08,796
Dreadful woman.

846
00:51:08,916 --> 00:51:12,076
No, it wasn't me.
Someone sent Sybil and Tom

847
00:51:12,076 --> 00:51:13,956
the price for the tickets to come over.

848
00:51:13,956 --> 00:51:17,716
Does it matter who it was? It
meant we could be at the wedding.

849
00:51:17,716 --> 00:51:21,356
Of course I wish it had been
you, Papa. But I don't mind.

850
00:51:21,356 --> 00:51:23,276
I thank them, whoever they are.

851
00:51:23,276 --> 00:51:27,436
Well, I'm very glad you're here, but
it wasn't me either, I'm sad to say.

852
00:51:27,436 --> 00:51:30,196
I love a mystery. Who could it be?

853
00:51:30,196 --> 00:51:33,516
My guess is cousin Isobel. She
always likes to stick her oar in.

854
00:51:33,516 --> 00:51:35,316
I'm going to ask her.

855
00:51:35,316 --> 00:51:37,316
For heaven's sake. It was me.

856
00:51:41,156 --> 00:51:43,636
You? But it wasn't your writing.

857
00:51:43,636 --> 00:51:45,676
No. Smithers did it.

858
00:51:45,676 --> 00:51:48,276
Like all ladies' maids
she lives for intrigue.

859
00:51:48,276 --> 00:51:50,156
You wanted me to come here?

860
00:51:50,156 --> 00:51:54,596
I wanted Sybil and her husband to
be here for Mary's wedding, yes.

861
00:51:55,516 --> 00:51:57,516
Why keep that secret?

862
00:51:58,156 --> 00:51:59,996
Silly, wasn't it?

863
00:51:59,996 --> 00:52:02,396
I'm very touched. I'll admit it.

864
00:52:02,396 --> 00:52:04,676
How democratic.

865
00:52:04,676 --> 00:52:07,276
Makes me think maybe I
have been mistaken in you.

866
00:52:07,716 --> 00:52:09,676
I am a woman of many parts.

867
00:52:10,716 --> 00:52:14,076
After all, Branson is... I mean, Tom...

868
00:52:14,596 --> 00:52:16,636
You're a member of the family now.

869
00:52:16,636 --> 00:52:19,196
You'll find we Crawleys stick together.

870
00:52:19,876 --> 00:52:23,316
Not always. Mary, what is it?

871
00:52:23,316 --> 00:52:25,316
Nothing, it's just...

872
00:52:27,716 --> 00:52:29,716
Oh, Mary.

873
00:52:34,036 --> 00:52:37,036
Oh, there you are. That's
all for this course.

874
00:52:37,516 --> 00:52:39,516
Don't you think, Daisy?

875
00:52:40,036 --> 00:52:42,596
Is Daisy all right, Mrs Patmore? Oh, yes.

876
00:52:42,596 --> 00:52:44,636
She's been such a big help.

877
00:52:44,636 --> 00:52:47,996
Now, I think we should
check the pudding, Daisy.

878
00:52:47,996 --> 00:52:50,036
Don't you agree?

879
00:52:50,036 --> 00:52:53,876
It's nerves. Everyone cries at
some point before their wedding.

880
00:52:53,876 --> 00:52:55,956
But what was the quarrel about?

881
00:52:55,956 --> 00:52:59,956
I'm not sure. I know she accused
him of not being on our side.

882
00:52:59,956 --> 00:53:01,796
Oh, well, I hope she's wrong.

883
00:53:01,796 --> 00:53:03,556
That could be rather serious.

884
00:53:03,556 --> 00:53:06,996
Of course he's on our side. It's
ridiculous. I'll go and see him.

885
00:53:06,996 --> 00:53:11,036
No, I'll go. I'm his best
man. I should be the one to go.

886
00:53:11,316 --> 00:53:14,836
What? I know what it is
to marry into this family.

887
00:53:14,836 --> 00:53:16,956
I'm not comparing myself to Mr Crawley,

888
00:53:16,956 --> 00:53:19,516
but he is another kind of
outsider. Well, I hardly...

889
00:53:19,516 --> 00:53:21,916
Well, why not? He's the
one who'll lose his job

890
00:53:21,916 --> 00:53:23,916
if the wedding's cancelled.

891
00:53:28,036 --> 00:53:31,316
I see what you're doing,
you know? What's that, then?

892
00:53:31,836 --> 00:53:34,076
Not responding to my protest.

893
00:53:34,076 --> 00:53:36,556
Oh... 'Not responding to my protest.'

894
00:53:36,556 --> 00:53:38,596
Very elegant, I must say.

895
00:53:38,596 --> 00:53:40,436
Who've you been talking to?

896
00:53:40,436 --> 00:53:42,556
Thomas? Well...

897
00:53:44,636 --> 00:53:46,756
Oh, just give me the cloth and I'll dry.

898
00:53:53,196 --> 00:53:56,676
Suppose he never gets the
money... It's not about the money.

899
00:53:56,676 --> 00:53:59,236
It's that he won't save Papa when he could.

900
00:54:01,036 --> 00:54:03,076
But he has to be true to himself.

901
00:54:03,076 --> 00:54:06,916
That's the point. He puts
himself above the rest of us.

902
00:54:06,916 --> 00:54:08,916
Don't you see?

903
00:54:09,356 --> 00:54:12,156
What I see is a good man, my lady.

904
00:54:13,196 --> 00:54:15,196
And they're not like buses.

905
00:54:15,196 --> 00:54:18,196
There won't be another one
along in ten minutes' time.

906
00:54:29,076 --> 00:54:31,076
It seems big, but it's not big.

907
00:54:32,796 --> 00:54:34,756
And if it happens?

908
00:54:34,756 --> 00:54:36,876
I get the money.

909
00:54:36,876 --> 00:54:38,876
I can't do what she wants.

910
00:54:39,436 --> 00:54:43,716
It's strange for me to be arguing about
inherited money and saving estates.

911
00:54:43,836 --> 00:54:47,116
When the old me would like to
put a bomb under the lot of you.

912
00:54:47,596 --> 00:54:51,036
But? But you're meant to be together.

913
00:54:51,996 --> 00:54:54,676
I've known that as long
as I've been at the house.

914
00:54:54,676 --> 00:54:58,076
And at first this kept you apart
and then that kept you apart.

915
00:54:59,596 --> 00:55:01,676
But please don't risk it a third time.

916
00:55:02,476 --> 00:55:04,476
Because I'll tell you this.

917
00:55:04,876 --> 00:55:08,396
You won't be happy with anyone else
while Lady Mary walks the earth.

918
00:55:08,996 --> 00:55:11,716
Call her Mary, please.
Never mind what I call her.

919
00:55:12,516 --> 00:55:16,556
I know what I'll call you if you let
this chance slip through your fingers.

920
00:55:18,876 --> 00:55:20,756
(KNOCK AT DOOR)

921
00:55:30,316 --> 00:55:33,956
I just need a word. No. Go away.

922
00:55:33,956 --> 00:55:36,116
I'm undressed. You can't come in.

923
00:55:36,116 --> 00:55:38,636
One word. Come to the door.

924
00:55:38,636 --> 00:55:41,516
Please. Just give him this chance.

925
00:55:42,196 --> 00:55:44,916
I won't look at you. It'd
be unlucky if you did.

926
00:55:45,636 --> 00:55:47,636
Only if we were getting married.

927
00:55:48,276 --> 00:55:50,276
Which we are.

928
00:56:00,556 --> 00:56:03,956
My darling, I refuse to quarrel
about something that hasn't happened

929
00:56:03,956 --> 00:56:05,716
and probably never will.

930
00:56:05,716 --> 00:56:07,716
That's what Anna says.

931
00:56:08,196 --> 00:56:10,196
Then she's right.

932
00:56:11,316 --> 00:56:16,076
My darling, I'm sure we will fight
about money and about Downton,

933
00:56:17,036 --> 00:56:19,956
about how to rear our children,
about any number of things.

934
00:56:19,956 --> 00:56:22,796
Then shouldn't we accept it?

935
00:56:22,796 --> 00:56:25,156
Matthew, I've been thinking...

936
00:56:25,756 --> 00:56:28,076
And I'm not angry now, truly I'm not.

937
00:56:28,956 --> 00:56:32,396
But if we can disagree over
something as fundamental as this,

938
00:56:32,396 --> 00:56:35,796
then shouldn't we be
brave and back away now?

939
00:56:36,476 --> 00:56:38,276
No.

940
00:56:38,276 --> 00:56:41,876
It's not because you're afraid of
calling it off? Because I'm not.

941
00:56:41,876 --> 00:56:43,876
No.

942
00:56:44,396 --> 00:56:46,396
It's because of something Tom said.

943
00:56:49,276 --> 00:56:53,396
That I would never be happy with anyone
else as long as you walked the earth.

944
00:56:53,676 --> 00:56:55,676
Which is true.

945
00:56:56,916 --> 00:57:00,916
And I think you feel the same about me.

946
00:57:08,836 --> 00:57:10,836
Can I kiss you?

947
00:57:12,076 --> 00:57:14,076
Because I need to.

948
00:57:14,916 --> 00:57:18,436
Very much. No. It's bad luck to look at me.

949
00:57:19,396 --> 00:57:21,716
What about if I close
my eyes and you do too?

950
00:57:26,116 --> 00:57:28,156
All right.

951
00:57:28,156 --> 00:57:30,156
But you mustn't cheat.

952
00:57:57,956 --> 00:57:59,956
Good night.

953
00:58:17,608 --> 00:58:19,928
Right, I'm off to collect Matthew.

954
00:58:19,928 --> 00:58:24,128
You look very smart. I hope so.
Because I'm extremely uncomfortable.

955
00:58:25,488 --> 00:58:27,488
Branson...

956
00:58:28,608 --> 00:58:30,608
That is, Tom.

957
00:58:31,888 --> 00:58:35,728
I want to thank you for what you did
last night. I'm grateful. I mean it.

958
00:58:35,728 --> 00:58:37,528
They're both strong characters.

959
00:58:37,528 --> 00:58:41,448
I'd say we have plenty of slamming
doors and shouting matches to come.

960
00:58:42,888 --> 00:58:44,888
Forgive me, I was about to be indignant,

961
00:58:44,888 --> 00:58:47,408
but you have a perfect
right to speak as you do.

962
00:58:47,688 --> 00:58:49,608
I hope you mean that too.

963
00:58:49,608 --> 00:58:51,568
I do.

964
00:58:51,568 --> 00:58:53,568
Now, hurry up.

965
00:58:54,968 --> 00:58:58,688
You'd ask if there was anything
you wanted me to tell you.

966
00:58:59,048 --> 00:59:02,368
I mean, I'm sure you
know. More than you did.

967
00:59:02,368 --> 00:59:05,528
And relax. There isn't
anything I need to hear now.

968
00:59:05,528 --> 00:59:09,568
Because when two people love each
other, you understand, everything...

969
00:59:12,128 --> 00:59:14,128
It's the most terrific fun.

970
00:59:14,688 --> 00:59:16,728
Careful, Mama, or you'll shock Anna.

971
00:59:17,408 --> 00:59:21,928
I'm a married woman now, my
lady. I think we should go.

972
00:59:21,928 --> 00:59:24,808
What about Anna? How are you
going to get to the church?

973
00:59:24,808 --> 00:59:26,808
They're waiting for me in the wagonette.

974
00:59:26,808 --> 00:59:28,808
I'll see you there.

975
00:59:30,128 --> 00:59:32,928
I know mine was a wild
runaway marriage, darling.

976
00:59:33,848 --> 00:59:36,048
And yours is the one everyone wanted.

977
00:59:36,048 --> 00:59:40,568
What's so thrilling is that
this is every bit as romantic.

978
00:59:41,248 --> 00:59:43,888
Thank you, for always being so sweet.

979
00:59:50,048 --> 00:59:54,768
Love and position in one handsome
package. Who could ask for more?

980
00:59:59,488 --> 01:00:01,488
Never mind Edith.

981
01:00:03,128 --> 01:00:07,728
Well, very, very good
luck, my beautiful daughter.

982
01:00:21,848 --> 01:00:26,408
Now, you've a great big porter cab
all to yourselves. Think of that.

983
01:00:26,408 --> 01:00:30,408
So we'll expect you to behave
as if you were quite grown up.

984
01:00:30,408 --> 01:00:32,408
You can do that, can't you?

985
01:00:33,088 --> 01:00:34,928
Got everything you need? Yes.

986
01:00:34,928 --> 01:00:36,928
Hop in, then.

987
01:00:37,208 --> 01:00:39,208
Careful with your dress.

988
01:00:41,568 --> 01:00:43,448
(GIRLS LAUGHING) Settle down.

989
01:00:43,448 --> 01:00:45,448
All right?

990
01:00:47,088 --> 01:00:49,368
Don't do anything I wouldn't do. Bye.

991
01:00:51,488 --> 01:00:54,328
Bye-bye. Good luck!

992
01:01:05,088 --> 01:01:07,088
Have you got everything you need? We do.

993
01:01:07,088 --> 01:01:10,008
Now, be off with you and enjoy yourself.

994
01:01:11,048 --> 01:01:12,888
I wish we were going.

995
01:01:12,888 --> 01:01:15,608
Who'll get the food ready
for when they come back?

996
01:01:15,768 --> 01:01:18,208
Still, fetch your coat
and we'll see her off.

997
01:01:21,568 --> 01:01:23,808
Right, see you in a minute.

998
01:01:28,488 --> 01:01:31,568
We're just leaving now, my
lord. As soon as we've got Anna.

999
01:01:31,568 --> 01:01:33,568
Here comes the bride.

1000
01:02:01,248 --> 01:02:03,248
Will I do, Carson?

1001
01:02:05,288 --> 01:02:07,288
Very nicely, my lady.

1002
01:02:13,088 --> 01:02:16,528
Thank heavens you got everything
settled. You had me worried.

1003
01:02:16,528 --> 01:02:20,088
It's not quite settled, I'm afraid.
He won't get off that easily.

1004
01:02:21,088 --> 01:02:23,088
But you're happy?

1005
01:02:23,088 --> 01:02:25,088
I am.

1006
01:02:25,568 --> 01:02:27,568
And what about you?

1007
01:02:29,488 --> 01:02:35,168
I'm so happy, so very happy,
I feel my chest will explode.

1008
01:02:53,848 --> 01:02:56,288
It's so lovely that you're
here. Come behind us.

1009
01:02:56,288 --> 01:02:59,448
I can't. I'm not family.
But you almost are.

1010
01:03:02,488 --> 01:03:04,888
Morning. Thank you.

1011
01:03:07,728 --> 01:03:11,088
Molesley, I'm very grateful to you

1012
01:03:11,088 --> 01:03:13,128
for keeping Mr Branson up to the mark.

1013
01:03:13,528 --> 01:03:16,408
We both are, aren't we? We certainly are.

1014
01:03:17,168 --> 01:03:19,168
Thank you, sir.

1015
01:03:25,088 --> 01:03:27,688
This is a proud day, Mrs Hughes.

1016
01:03:28,288 --> 01:03:32,248
I don't know if I'm proud, but I'm
very glad you're happy, Mr Carson.

1017
01:03:33,328 --> 01:03:36,568
You're next, darling, you'll see. Will I?

1018
01:03:36,568 --> 01:03:39,768
So encouraging to see the future unfurl.

1019
01:03:41,568 --> 01:03:46,408
As long as you remember it will
bear no resemblance to the past.

1020
01:03:47,168 --> 01:03:49,168
(CHEERING)

1021
01:04:29,208 --> 01:04:31,008
(CHEERING OUTSIDE)

1022
01:04:35,848 --> 01:04:37,848
(ORGAN PLAYING) Good luck.

1023
01:05:14,488 --> 01:05:16,488
You came.

1024
01:05:17,248 --> 01:05:19,968
To be honest, I wasn't
completely sure you would.

1025
01:05:20,288 --> 01:05:23,968
I'm glad to hear it. I
should hate to be predictable.

1026
01:05:28,048 --> 01:05:30,528
I'm sorry, it still seems
odd to be found in your bed.

1027
01:05:30,528 --> 01:05:33,688
Isn't it dangerous to let this
Strallan nonsense simmer on?

1028
01:05:33,688 --> 01:05:35,448
Ask him to end it.

1029
01:05:35,448 --> 01:05:38,168
Somehow the poor chap managed
to burn a hole in my tails.

1030
01:05:38,168 --> 01:05:40,968
This is what comes of making
him run before he could walk.

1031
01:05:40,968 --> 01:05:43,088
We've 20 lords and
ladies in the drawing room

1032
01:05:43,088 --> 01:05:45,088
and we've got no dinner to give them.

1033
01:05:45,568 --> 01:05:49,648
TOGETHER: # Let me call you 'sweetheart'

1034
01:05:49,648 --> 01:05:51,648
♪ I'm in love with...

1035
01:05:53,048 --> 01:05:56,968
His lordship's in trouble. He thinks
he may have to sell. Sell Downton?

1036
01:05:57,808 --> 01:05:59,808
itfc subtitles