Do you ever thought
about who you want to date?
Ever since I got here,
I've been thinking
about who I wanna date.
- Does that include me? No.
- Sure.
I was shocked that
he's been thinking about me,
I love him more than ever.
[Jose] I would love to go on
a date or something.
I like Soyoung a lot,
but Shannon
is a very special woman,
and I would love
to get to know each other
a little bit deeper.
How do you feel when you see
the exterior of me,
being an older woman?
I mean, I see your elegance.
All right, I'll take that.
Jose is hard to figure out.
I feel like he may
give everyone that
kind of attention,
so you don't know
if you're special.
[Ryan] Let's make a bet.
Gabriel can't come
to your room
for one solid day.
Oh my God.
[laughs]
I know Gabriel
feels threatened, but I'm not.
[Stefany speaking]
It's so unattractive
being controlling and stuff,
and I felt like that's such
a weird way of looking
at things.
The results
of the chemistry tests are in.
[gasping]
There's one mother and son
that scored the lowest.
- [Lisa] Oh.
- And they will be going home.
Oh.
April and Ricky, it's time
for you to leave the villa.
- Oh, no.
- Wow.
It just got real.
[indistinct chatter]
[doorbell ringing]
[indistinct shouting]
What, a new mom and son,
what the hell is going on?
Oh, my God,
you have to be kidding me.
- Oh.
- Oh, my God.
A new mom.
Holy [bleep] I wasn't
expecting this at all.
[indistinct chatter]
Oh, my God.
Hi.
Hello.
- What's your name?
- Lisa.
Joey, nice to meet you man.
- What's your name?
- Ryan, hi.
Ryan, oh, we got
two Ryans now.
Oh, there are two Ryans,
all right.
It hasn't even been
a full 24 hours that April
and Ricky are gone,
and now we have newcomers.
Hey, Ryan,
nice meeting you.
[Shannan] Like, we have
no idea what to expect
at any given time.
Plus, I don't know them.
- Look like really,
really nice people.
- Yeah.
So, like, I don't know
if they can handle everything
that's been going on
in the house already.
Like... I'm like,
are they ready
to sign up for this crazy?
Sorry, but what's your name?
- Stefany.
- Stefany, Lisa.
Stefany, I will remember,
okay, oh my God.
[Kelle] Well, lo and behold,
we have two newcomers,
and I'm thinking,
I'm wearing a bikini,
and she's wearing a mu-mu,
no competition.
- Hi, how you doing?
- April.
April, I'm born in April,
I can remember your name.
[indistinct shouting]
Good God!
I'm Ryan, and this is
my beautiful mom, Lisa.
Aw, thank you, honey.
- Nice to meet you.
- [Lisa speaking]
I know, I wanted
to do it again, yeah.
My mom's big personality
is definitely something
that stands out.
She used to be an actress back
in the '80s and '90s
and still has that
big outgoing personality.
Ryan two, Ryan two.
Ryan... oh, man,
okay, it's a great name.
[Lisa] Ryan is just
this all-around guy,
he's amazingly artistic,
he paints and he composes
classical music.
I mean,
he's absolutely amazing.
I came on this retreat
to really spend
some quality time
with my son and also for us
both to be looking for love
at the same time.
And maybe the missing piece
is that I've needed
his opinion the whole time.
[laughing]
You guys give us
one second here, one second.
So just occurred to me,
you may not have any idea...
- what's going on.
- [indistinct chatter]
Yeah, so welcome,
you are on a dating retreat.
- Yes, we know that.
- Okay.
- Okay, we know that much.
- We're here... We're all moms.
...we get to spend...
Yeah. Okay, all moms,
with your sons.
- And these are our sons.
- With your sons, got it.
Yes.
And the purpose is to get
to know the sons.
And to break
the age barriers.
- And the purpose for you...
- Age is just a number.
- ...is to get to know
the moms.
- Right.
Okay.
And be open.
[laughing]
I'm just trying to get
a lay of the land, and like,
I didn't know all the moms
were going to be here.
It's the mom's sons
that is the dating pool.
I thought it was going to be
other people, other guys.
Let's go take out to the bar
and get a drink,
everybody can come.
[Ryan] Yes, please, necessary.
So, I'm meeting a potential,
and then the mom, so very...
very interesting,
what can I say?
[Jose] Tell me if you want
one more tequila.
[Lisa] Thank you.
- Gracias...
- [Jose] Salud.
- Okay.
- That is our
resident bartender.
[Lisa] Oh, okay.
What do you make with that?
- He does a great job
of making...
- [Jose] Magic.
Yeah, he does, he really...
it really is magic.
And this is
a grapefruit, correct?
Yes.
- Yeah, oh,
I love grapefruit...
- [Shannan] Yeah.
- ...because it's so sour...
- Yeah, pretty sure.
...in my opinion.
[Jose] The balance
is sweetness,
you look like
you're very sweet,
so... so the balance
is sweetness.
[laughs]
You're good, I look sweet.
[Lisa speaking]
He's adorable.
I am 1,000% sure that Lisa
is going to be taken
in by Jose's good looks
and charm,
you know, Mr. Charismatic,
but I'm not giving up on Jose,
he's my... my one and only,
and so I need to make sure
that there's not too much
face time with the new girl.
So, like, have you dated
younger guys before?
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah, how young?
27 years younger.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
I find younger men
better in the bedroom.
Do you want
a grapefruit drink?
I think I would
like that, please.
- Let me find the shaker.
- Okay.
[Lisa] Older men have
an insecurity about them,
it's kind of annoying,
it's like
they needed constant,
like, you know,
like being a mom to them.
Oh, honey, you look fine,
it's okay, I know
your hair's receding,
it happens.
Look what's happening to me,
you know... I don't know.
So, they needed more,
like, coddling.
Where do you live?
I live in Boston,
but I'm a senior engineer, so.
Okay, wow.
Oh, it's nice,
very, very smart.
Engineer,
what kind of engineer?
- I'm a software engineer.
- Okay.
Yeah, mostly like
machine learning,
artificial intelligence,
and stuff.
Okay, okay.
[Stefany] I usually
date professionals,
so it's great to hear
that Ryan
actually has
an amazing career.
I mean, he seems pretty mature
for his age,
and I'm excited
to get to know him.
This is nice.
Thanks so much.
[Stefany] Yeah, it's nice.
[Ryan S] I do feel
a little bit like
I've been tossed
into the deep end.
[Ryan S speaking]
...but the first one
who catches my eye
is Stefany,
she is really pretty,
dressed in kind of
a classy way.
It seems like someone
I maybe want to get
to know better,
interest is big for me.
So, who are you
taking out first?
You.
[laughing]
Oh, he's going
to take me out first.
[Ryan] I think Stefany
needs that attention.
I think it's her dream
to have, like,
men fight over her.
See, I knew it, I knew it.
[Ryan] With Stefany...
Internally, I'm... I'm
pretty much super over it.
So I need an answer,
that's what I need
from Stefany right now.
Is she here to date me,
is she interested in getting
to know me better
on that level or not?
The new Ryan wants
to take me out.
- Does he really?
- Yeah.
That's annoying...
[Gabriel speaking]
[Gabriel] At this point,
I would say Stefany
and I's connection
is the strongest it's been,
you know the new Ryan
can try and take her on a date
but she does like me
and I like her
and I think
that's unbreakable.
Do you still love me?
Uh-oh, I have competition.
What happened?
From what I can see,
it seems like Stefany
and Gabriel really have
a connection there.
And so, I'm like, okay,
I'm not going to put my eggs
in that basket.
[Stefany] Come on.
- Cheers.
Aa-ha, salud.
[cell phone vibrating]
Oh, hey, guys, I got a text.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- All right.
- Here we go.
[Charlene] Welcome
to the villa, Lisa, and Ryan.
We have an activity plan
that is sure to get you
well acquainted
with the other moms and sons.
Guys always think they know
what you want in the bedroom.
Facts.
But do they really?
The truth is, if anyone knows
about sex, it's us ladies.
You have the age, wisdom,
and experience,
and now we are giving you
the opportunity
to share that carnal knowledge
with your sons.
- No.
- Oh, I'm not.
Head inside, it's time
to teach these
young guys a lesson.
[indistinct chatter]
A lesson.
No books and pencil
sharpen for class,
because the teacher is here.
I think that Ryan and I have
a very open relationship,
but there are boundaries.
Yeah.
And I accidentally walked
in the room at time
and something like...
You have not.
I was a married woman.
Either way...
[Ryan speaking]
...that's all I know.
[Kelle] Oh, my God.
Ew.
[Kelle] Sex ed.
The whole internal organs.
We're walking in,
and there's like, sex toys...
- [Stefany] A little graphic.
- Yeah.
[Stefany] Definitely.
[Gabriel] Oh, my God.
Oh, we got a crisp show.
- Ew.
- All right.
I'm really excited about
the sex ed class,
because older women definitely
are more advanced
in the bedroom,
we can teach a few things.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh.
Oh, my land, oh, my land,
this is going too far
and I don't want
to see that, you know.
Oh, my Lord.
I'm a big fan of oral,
so I'm going to bring
in an orange,
delicious kind of fruit.
[laughing]
Charlene is so turned on,
she might just, like, take him
on the table right now.
Yeah, well that just straight
came out of nowhere.
That was like...
[Gabriel speaking]
Okay.
I see myself being
a potential match
with Stefany,
but the elephant in the room
is her relationship
with Gabriel.
You're the only person [bleep]
like, somebody in this house.
You're heated.
[indistinct chatter]
Oh, my.
[Jose] In the table,
there's many things,
all sorts of toys
and things over there,
so some people
are going to have fun.
- [cell phone vibrating]
- Are you guys ready?
Yes.
Okay, it's time
for some sex ed.
- Moms.
- Yes.
Please take turns
selecting questions
and quizzing your sons.
Oh.
I don't want to go up.
Be sure to use all the props
by the end of this lesson.
All the props.
Let's hope some
of you can enjoy
the fruits of your labor.
[producer speaking]
- No.
- [producer] With Joey?
- Mmm-mmm.
- No, we never...
- [Kelle speaking]
- We never heard
of birds and bees talk.
- [Kelle speaking]
- Bro, oh my God.
With the internet nowadays,
and my friends...
come on,
how did you figure it out?
Oh, all right,
stop it, stop it.
- I'll go first.
- Okay.
- Go for it.
- Take it easy on them.
Yeah.
[laughs]
I'm ditching class.
I think sex talks should
definitely be kept to yourself
or with your partner.
I don't think it should be
discussed in public
or just with your kids.
I rather just go to God
with all those crazy thoughts
that, you know,
come to your mind.
You know, what do you think?
No, I agree.
- I guess.
- Yeah.
So, I'm going to pick Jose.
[indistinct shouting]
- [indistinct]
- Jose!
Go on up, Jose.
- Ready?
- All right, Jose.
Ready or not, you're coming,
so it's fine.
I really think Billy is great,
but I picked Jose,
because I'm actually curious
to know how much
he actually knows
in the bedroom.
What really turns
a woman on the most?
Oh.
- Come on, Jose, you got this.
- Look at your...
- [Ryan speaking]
- [Kelle] Look at your section.
Look at your
arsenal right now.
Don't dig too deep,
pun intended.
[bleep] Okay.
- Point at... point...
- [Ryan] You got
to point to it.
You can use any of these
and it will be here.
[laughing]
- [Kelle speaking]
- No. No, I wouldn't use this.
But this is what I'm asking,
your... your question.
What turns a woman
on the most?
[April] Jose is really pretty
to look at,
but I'm wondering maybe
if he does need to be
schooled in this area?
I don't know.
Just tell me what pleases
the woman the most.
When I'm... when...
well, in sexual intercourse,
when a man finds her spot.
Okay.
I'm learning, Jose might be
a little clueless,
he needs some education.
How would you answer
the question?
It all starts with a touch.
- It starts with a kiss.
- It all starts with a touch.
[Lisa] It's almost like
you want the woman to say,
please go there, please...
- You shouldn't have to ask.
- Could you there now?
You may have to tease,
it's a tease,
whether it's a kiss
or the arms
or hands or whatever,
and you're getting there
and then you're not
going there,
and then you want the woman
to, like, be begging.
[Charlene] Oh, this is why
I stay single,
and this is why I have
a hard time dating,
because imagine getting
in the bedroom to that.
These guys really need
to go to class.
Welcome class,
welcome students,
fellow teachers.
- I would like my son
to answer...
- What?
[Charlene] ...the question, because...
- How did you pick me?
- [Charlene] Why not?
Harrison, I've heard things,
he's got the goods.
It's my job to make sure
he knows what to do with it.
My sex life is very private.
I have faith in you.
[Harrison] This is going
to be uncomfortable.
[Charlene] Where is the labia?
Oh.
[Charlene] He better know.
[Harrison] I don't...
Let me give you a hint, bro.
No, don't tell.
Okay, no.
[indistinct chatter]
[Charlene] No, no, no, no,
Harrison, that's not right,
try again.
- So...
- [Charlene speaking]
- Cervical lips.
- Yes.
Yeah, okay.
And the teat.
If you were in this zone...
[April speaking]
Yeah, because I give birth
all the time.
- Well...
- Well, it's open.
I can't believe that
he doesn't know
the other parts of the vagina.
- God.
- I'm done.
Too much.
All you need to know
is where to put it,
you don't need to know
all the... the part names
and get down there
with a microscope.
And, hey, this is that,
this is this,
this is that, no.
This is so important,
because the bedroom,
everything leads
to the bedroom
and we need
to please each other,
Because if not, this is where
we're going.
So, you... even men to talk
about how they wanted
to be touched,
what you guys like.
Come on, guys,
everything is all about sex,
this whole experience
is about sex,
so we need to talk about sex.
Am I right? Come on guys.
Come on, where my ladies
are, right, right, come on.
[indistinct shouting]
Long live the penis,
guys, long live the penis.
I am really surprised to see
just how passionate Charlene
is about this sex discussion.
She really cares about people
having, you know,
pleasure in the bedroom,
and I think that's, you know,
it was a shock,
but also, like, honestly,
it makes me more interested
to get to know her.
Ryan, come on, now.
Let's go, Ryan.
Come on down.
Come on, Ryan.
What do you think
is a woman's favorite
type of foreplay?
- Hm.
- Hmm.
Demonstrate your go
to foreplay technique
on one of these fruits.
Okay.
I'm a big fan of oral,
so I'm going to bring
in orange,
delicious kind of fruit.
[laughing]
- Technique.
- Oh, yeah.
[laughing]
Oh, yeah.
[Lisa] Seeing my son
demonstrate his skill set,
he's very much
like a professor.
Now, fortunately,
Charlene's head
was right in the way,
that was good.
I didn't have to turn
my head because
it was already blocked.
He's doing a good job.
I'm not watching.
[Stefany speaking]
Ryan as his technique
with the orange,
I think Charlene
is so turned on,
she might just, like take him
on the table right now.
- [Joey] Yeah, well that just
straight came out of nowhere.
- That is like...
That was like, you expect him
to be like... kind of like
the nerdiest kid,
and then he starts going down
on the food like,
you've never seen before.
I mean, who are you, really?
Great explanation.
Great demonstration.
[Soyoung speaking]
If he could do that,
I mean, he could make
a woman happy, right?
I want to see Jose doing it.
Okay. Eenie, meenie,
miney, mo.
I pick Jimmy.
Okay. Okay.
- Me and my mom
were really open...
- That's my son.
...very young.
Like my mom said
"anything you want
to know" I was like,
less than ten, I'm like,
"Mom, I don't even
never kissed a girl before."
She was like,
"whatever you need to know,"
I'm like, "All right."
- He is so horny.
- Hm?
Finishing on a woman's face,
do they find it sexy?
Oh, I would say that's like
less than a 50% ratio,
I say aim for the, you know...
- [Soyoung speaking]
- Aim for the breast
or... or down.
A man finishing
on the face of a woman,
do women like that?
- And...
- I don't know.
Yeah, I think
they don't mind at all.
There's your answer.
- We need you to pick
one more question.
- You need permission.
- You always need permission
to do that.
- You need the permission.
- Yeah, you do.
- Whoa!
[Stefany speaking]
I can't sit there.
[Jimmy] Is it that boring?
Damn, I thought
this was pretty exciting.
I'm sorry, there's no way.
It was just too intense, like,
I don't want to know about
what you do to women,
it's just too much.
I honestly couldn't do it.
I'm going to my room,
I'm going to my room.
Lo and behold,
Stefany, she walks away,
Gabriel obviously follows.
I'm calling the bluff,
Gabriel and Stefany
are not as innocent
as they seem.
Agreed.
We're adults here, right,
you guys aren't like,
14 years old.
For me, this isn't fringy
or dirty or anything,
it's part of living.
It's a natural thing
that everyone does,
like it's not taboo
in my house.
So, when Stefany and Gabriel
just kind of run away
like that, they're really
not open to learning
and growing.
At the end of the day,
as you mature,
it's about connectivity.
Everyone thinks like, oh,
after menopause
or whatever like,
woman is going to be dry.
My experience, absolutely not,
absolutely not.
I'm as sexual as I was
in my teens, you know.
I'm enlightened
from this class,
I learned a lot.
[producer speaking]
Ah, I definitely got
a lot of tips and tricks
that could... that could maybe
go into the bedroom, too.
Tips and tricks.
Class dismissed.
[indistinct shouting]
[Jimmy] I orgasmed
three times during this class,
- y'all didn't even know.
- [laughing]
Okay, I can be here
and you guys can be there,
but some people
are going to be like,
in direct sun
if you don't care.
[Gabriel speaking]
Okay.
Stefany specifically told me
that she does not want
to date Gabriel.
Oh, come on mama.
How are you feeling
about Gabriel, honestly?
I mean, he's funny,
but like more friends,
I think.
[Ryan] She said
this man is 23,
she doesn't see him
in that light,
but he's lying on you
on the couch.
[Ryan speaking]
Why are you heated, Ryan?
[Gabriel] I think
his attitude is just
a little too aggro for me.
And there's really no need
for this intense jealousy.
You guys made a bet,
she didn't wake up
at 5:00 a.m.,
what was that about?
I'll tell you after I change
my clothes,
unless you want to talk now.
Why am I with her,
I thought it was...
I'm not supposed to be next
to her for 24 hours.
All right, let's make a bet.
You tell me what's the bet?
All right, Gabriel can't come
to your room
for one solid day.
Oh, my God.
- [laughs]
- I get a full day.
Stefany shared an intimate,
private conversation
because she's an instigator.
I don't like the fact that
I feel like Stefany
runs around behind
people's backs
and then starts narratives.
Maybe I'm going to change
to take her class.
Oh, you should take it,
she's great.
Yeah.
Stefany always leaves
at the right moment, right?
You're heated.
You're the only person [bleep]
somebody in this house.
I see myself being
a potential match
with Stefany,
but the elephant in the room
is her relationship
with Gabriel.
I don't have [bleep] to say.
When I walk away,
dare she not going to say
to me when I get back.
I don't like him.
Camaraderie.
[Billy] I think Ryan
was being a little weird,
and just trying
to claim my mom
and steal her away
from Gabriel.
You pissed them off for sure.
But I didn't even...
did I instigate that?
[Stefany] I'm here to date
and see who I have
a connection with, that's it.
I have no idea why Ryan
thinks that I'm giving
anyone mixed signals.
Would you like to go on
a date with Ryan, if he asked?
Ah, right about now,
I don't want to go anywhere
with no one.
- Ready.
- Whoa-hu.
Today is a day
that I'm going to make
Jose be my man.
So, what do you all think
about Soyoung and Jose's date?
You all think
they're a good match...
- No, of course not.
- Really?
There's going to be
a lot of heartbreaks
between Jose and his woman.
[kissing]
I don't know why you keep
giving him energy,
stay out of each other's way.
Just stop coming around,
I don't come around him.
[Shannan] I'm going to call it
what I see,
I'm putting it on Stefany
because she's the more mature
of these two young men,
and I think that she's given
some mixed signals.
Stefany, you got a second?
- [Stefany] Yeah, babe.
- Come... come sit.
What happened?
So, I'm a...
I'm a problem solver,
that's what I do.
- And it don't work
without Gabriel.
- [Stefany] Same.
Okay, you have a second,
just have a sit.
- Same, I am like, so...
- Let's conclude this drama,
or whatever.
- Right?
- Question number one.
What's wrong?
Why is Gabe... you know
what's wrong, come on, dude.
Oh.
Why is Gabriel asking me
about the bet that
we made yesterday?
He overheard,
I was telling Billy.
[Stefany speaking]
[Billy speaking]
[Gabriel speaking]
You're not gonna
wake up at 5:00.
- [laughing]
- You're joking.
What I want
to make sure is that,
there are not mixed signals
going both ways, because...
There is not.
...what's happening is I see
Gabriel right here
laying all over you,
there's no boundaries
that are there.
No, the thing
with Gabriel is because, like,
we've established, like,
a friendship, I...
that's all it's been.
- Have you told Gabriel...
- [Stefany] He knows.
- ...that you feel like
he's just a friend?
- He knows.
- How does he know?
- He knows, he...
[Ryan] No. No.
[Stefany] Yes,
he does know, bring him...
that's not true.
- And this is where
the problem stems?
- [Stefany] He knows.
[Ryan] I'm not buying
what she's selling.
No, you're lying.
Stop...
Straight fiction.
He and I
are good friends, like...
and I'm friends with...
Did you tell him that.
I... I feel like I'm friends
with you, too.
I don't want friends
that aren't truthful with me,
are you seeing
what I'm saying.
- How am I not truthful
to you, Ryan?
- I don't want...
Because I feel like
you spin stories.
How?
- Because...
- Okay, I'm not going
to do this.
Because he's acting crazy.
Okay, he's acting crazy,
but you're telling me,
I'm spinning stories.
Because you didn't ask
that question.
I'm okay,
I'm okay, whatever.
- Do you see...
- I'm done, I'm done.
[Ryan] It does not occur
to you?
[Stefany] Honestly,
I'm not doing this.
That was awkward,
he's talking to me
with his mom.
You know, he's pinpointing me
with his mom and saying
I'm creating this.
I... I honestly don't want
anything to do with it.
It's... it's just crazy,
it's crazy to me.
[Ryan] But it's coming
from you.
No, Ryan, I'm good.
I'm good.
- That's fine,
I'm... I'm better.
- [Stefany] I'm good.
I don't either.
[Stefany] It's freaking
ridiculous, [bleep] that.
- People show you who they are.
- [Ryan] Yes.
So, she just showed you
who she was.
Oh, you missed
all the [bleep] drama.
Shannon and Ryan
called me over,
he got mad because of the...
you laying on the couch,
you were leaning over.
Am I not allowed...
is he your girl...
are you, his girlfriend?
No.
[Gabriel] I know that
she likes me and I know
her and I are really going
somewhere with this.
And I think Ryan's feelings
are just a little hurt
because Stefany
and I are developing
such a strong connection.
You're a queen
- and you don't deserve
all this unneeded stress.
- Thank you.
I like hanging out
with Gabriel,
he's a gentleman.
You know, I like hanging out
with Ryan,
'cause we have
good conversations,
but I'm... I'm not
with anybody here,
I'm being clear
with both of...
I haven't made a decision
with anybody here.
[Jose speaking]
[indistinct chatter]
[Soyoung Speaking]
[Jose speaking]
Soyoung and I are going
to this whale shark
swimming experience
because Soyoung
asked me out
on a date last night.
I had a crush on you,
so would you like
to go on a date
with me one day?
I would love to, it will be
my pleasure and honor.
Okay, relief.
[Jose] I've wanted to ask her
on a date for a long time.
And she beat me to it.
I'm very excited
to sharing time with her
and getting to know her
a little bit more.
They swim very, very quick.
Today is the day that
I'm going to make Jose
to be my man.
[chuckles]
Welcome, everyone on board,
my name is Armando,
and I'm going...
I'm gonna be your guide.
So, we're going to do
the activity of swimming
with the whale shark.
- [Jose] Amazing. Okay.
- Sounds good.
- [Jose speaking]
- [Soyoung] Thank you.
Let me introduce you
to captain,
the captain is Roberto.
[speaking foreign language]
Bye-bye.
[Soyoung speaking]
[Jose speaking]
[Jose] I'm super excited.
[Soyoung speaking]
[Jose speaking]
- [Soyoung speaking]
- [Jose] Yeah.
Soyoung, is so playful
and so happy,
I see her spirit and I can
really connect with...
with her
and how she sees life,
and it's something that
I am really attracted to,
and I'm so happy
that I could be
sharing this with her.
Whale sharks are not whales
and not sharks,
it's actually a fish,
and this is the world's
largest fish, okay.
[Soyoung] This is
my first time ever swimming
with a whale shark.
I'm very excited, I don't know
what's going on,
but I am ready.
- Ready?
- [cheering]
Especially, you know,
Jose is gonna be next
to me, so I'm ready.
Go, go, go.
It really is amazing
to see the magnitude
of a whale shark, it's a once
in a lifetime experience.
- Soyoung.
- Yeah.
Huge.
Oh, my gosh,
look at her eyeballs.
Yeah.
It was unbelievable,
it was like I was in a dream.
I felt like I was getting
closer to him, you know,
and I shared
that moment with Jose.
Oh, what a life.
[cheering]
I just shared
something special
that I never shared
with anybody.
- Perfect.
- Yes. [indistinct]
Of course, and then... look.
[Armando speaking]
[indistinct shouting]
[Jose] Seeing the humpbacks
and having her by my side
really made that moment
a very special one for sure.
And it's something
we will never forget,
and it definitely
brought us closer together.
She is definitely the one that
I would be more interested
in exploring
and sharing a future with.
That's one for the books,
like for the rest of her life.
[Soyoung] I know, right?
That was awesome.
Thank you.
[kissing]
- Thank you.
- You are lovely.
[Soyoung speaking]
...but I could see
I could get serious with him.
[Soyoung speaking]
Thank you very much,
it was really special.
- You're really special.
- [Soyoung speaking]
Thank you, thank you,
thank you.
So, what do you all think
about Soyoung and Jose's date,
because they went
with a whale shark watching.
I mean... that's...
that's such an experience.
[Ryan S] I think they have
the best date so far.
To be honest,
let me just put it out there.
- Mmm-mmm.
- Please do, yeah.
Please do.
I have really
thoughtful dates with Jose.
We connect like
on a lot of different levels.
Jose is... is very kind
to everyone that he meets,
that's one of the qualities
I really, really
like about him.
But when it gets down to love,
you know, he and I have
some really
deeper connections.
I do just have just one life,
and I want to make
the most of it.
And... and there's a saying
in Spanish
[speaking foreign language]
Dude, that sounds sexy.
What does that mean?
It's basically
that nobody takes
your experience from you.
And so, I'm not really
worried about anybody else,
because I know
that our conversations
and our connection is special.
So, he and Soyoung,
that was... that was about
two people who are adventurous
and would have enjoyed
- just that, but that was...
- [Joey] Huh-huh.
But I haven't really
seen them, like,
talk much at all... at all.
Not like that,
not like that, nah.
So, you all think
they're a good match...
No, of course not, nah.
- Really?
- No.
And Jose is going on
a lot of dates with, you know,
almost every woman
in the house.
So, I'm just really wishing
that he's not a player
and he's trying
to play my mom,
and he's playing
Mr. Nice Guy just
to get everyone's attention.
Ah, I hope
that's not the case.
Each of the women that
I've dated here in the retreat
has something
very, very special.
I think the woman
that I'm connected
with the most has been...
You keep talking,
bro, what's the point?
- You haven't said [bleep]
- Stop talking
while I'm talking.
Tell me all about it.
Did you see the shark?
- The whale shark.
- [Pola] See.
Well, of course, yeah, we had
a very magical experience.
- It was?
- [Jose] Yeah, amazing.
So, we swam a couple of times
with the whale sharks...
Huh-huh.
...and then out of nowhere,
we saw a humpback whale.
No. No, no.
You didn't, you didn't.
Yeah, we really enjoyed
the moment a lot.
But do you feel that chemistry
between you and her?
She's amazing.
She showed me a different side
of her...
very playful side,
she laughed a lot,
she was very funny,
was very caring.
- I'm happy for you,
I'm happy for you.
- Thank you.
Each of the women that
I've dated here in the retreat
has something
very, very special,
and I've connected
in many different ways.
I think that the women
that I've connected
with the most
has been Soyoung.
Really?
- Yeah.
- Wow, Jose.
For sure, yeah.
- I wasn't expecting that.
- Really?
[Pola] Never.
Maybe you're not clear
that it's not her,
it's just everything
that you did with her.
I mean, if you take her
somewhere else,
do you think
you would be happy with her?
I don't know.
So, I see Jose
having great connection
with a lot of girls here,
even Kelle, I mean.
But I wouldn't think he would
get a connection with Soyoung.
Soyoung is amazing,
but I see it really
as friendship.
You know
who I would pick for Jose,
I really would pick Shannon.
Her conversations
are really serious,
and I feel Jose's
conversations are the same.
So, they have lots of things
to... to talk about.
Do you think Shannon
will be disappointed,
because I'm sure
she expects to you
to be close to her again.
I actually like Shannon a lot
and we have shared a lot.
Yeah, I see that.
I think it's just
a matter of...
just waiting for that spark
to happen, and I think...
I mean, I don't know,
it's... it's unexplainable,
it really is.
What I'm wondering right now
is that if that connection
with Soyoung was caused
from the euphoria
of the whole experience
and not necessarily
because of her.
If I went with Shannon
to that date,
would I feel the same way
about Shannon or not?
I think I need to give it
a little thought
and slow down a little bit,
because I need to see
how I'm feeling really.
- We'll have to wait and see.
- [Pola] Let's see, let's see.
I don't know.
[cell phone chiming]
You're going to like
this one, mamas.
Gators, get ready to go back
in time to when your moms
were your age.
Tonight, we're going to party
like it's 1990s something.
[all cheering]
It's a '90s dance
party tonight,
I'm super excited.
- [Kelle speaking]
- Yeah, yeah.
Show me your moves.
Oh, y'all gon' make me
take off my shoes.
[Charlene] This party is like
pre-Harrison time
and I'm just feeling
the moment of like
when I was 16.
I think I was negative
ten years old in the '90s.
I was still like a sperm
just sitting in the eggs.
Wow.
[Ryan] It's beginning to get
to a point where I feel like
consistently her
and Gabriel now,
like try to come around me
and do things
to disrespect me,
to bother me.
Hey, Stef, do you mind
if I borrow you for a minute.
- Yeah, what's up?
- Okay, cool.
- [Ryan speaking]
- Oh.
- Oh, I know.
- No, I'm really chilly.
- [Ryan speaking]
No, no, it's fine.
I need to know,
clearly, clear cut,
like straight to the point,
where does she stand?
Does she have a romantic
interest in me or not?
So how do you feel?
Hm, I feel fine,
but I just don't think
what happened earlier
was cool.
I'm blown away that your mom
was actually questioning me,
and that actually
was not cool with me.
It was never my intent
to ambush you.
But you know what,
it makes no sense, Ryan,
we never discussed
like we're an item.
Just because we went
on a one date.
- [Ryan] No.
- And we kissed.
That's your problem,
you're a liar.
Don't be rude to her.
Don't talk
to my girl like that.
I think your feelings are hurt
because she doesn't like it.
Then why did she kiss me
on the beach,
telling me that she doesn't
[bleep] you [bleep] me.
You know what,
it makes no sense, Ryan.
We went out, you gave me
a kiss, I kissed you back,
and that was it.
And then now saying that
I'm creating drama here.
Yes.
How am I creating drama?
By not telling
this dude or me,
the straight story.
What straight story.
Did you tell Gabriel,
what you told me
you feel about him?
I don't understand
why you're so fixated
with finding out
what I talk about Gabriel?
No, I'm...
Who do you think,
you think I'm sitting
over there kissing Gabriel
and telling him,
oh, I want to date you.
- I'm gonna be honest.
- I'm so happy...
I don't care what y'all do,
what I care about is this.
You clearly do,
because you're just thinking
that's what I'm doing.
I'm here to date and see
who I have a connection with,
and Ryan is pushing the issue
and moving way too fast.
He is ruining any connection
we could have.
I feel like you spun
me and Gabriel,
two separate stories,
why, because he's acting...
[Stefany] Let's bring him.
Let's bring him.
- [Ryan] You want that?
- Yeah.
- [Ryan] Bring him.
- Let's go.
Bring him.
Stefany, I don't think
she's told Gabriel
that she's not interested
in him romantically,
because I think
she likes the attention.
He's just making it seem
like I'm playing
both of you, basically.
- Oh.
- [Gabriel] You wanted to talk?
- What is the problem here?
- I don't understand it.
For starters, I did not ask
to have a talk
with the two of you.
I asked to have a talk
with Stefany...
Bro, can you just
get to the point?
I don't get it, it's like
you keep saying...
I'm as tired as,
one more time to keep
this bullshit [bleep]
going on.
This is so funny.
Bro, what the [bleep]
you keep talking, bro,
what's the point,
you haven't said [bleep]
Stop talking
while I'm talking.
Can I just say something
real quick?
Sure.
Bro, Stefany
and I have been vibing,
you're the only one causing
a problem here, to be real.
To be honest with you,
it takes more than one person
to call it a problem.
- I...
- But, Stefany...
like, have we been good?
I didn't ask you to ask her.
We didn't have one fight
until Ryan started, like, getting...
- I think because I went out...
- You didn't ask me to ask her.
- ...on a date with him, he...
- I didn't ask you to ask her,
when you asked me.
- It's like if you want advice
to, like...
- I don't want your advice.
- ...kind of like talk to her.
- Bro, I'll [bleep]
help you, like...
- You're not getting it.
Bro, you can take her
on a date, I don't...
we're not dating.
Brother, brother,
you're missing the point.
Stefany is her own woman,
it's like her and I...
we don't even know
if it's romantic yet
or something,
we're just vibing.
And then she's telling me
you made a bet with her,
like, oh, if you don't wake up
at 5:00 a.m.,
you can't be around Gabriel
for 24 hours.
It's like, what even
is that bet, bro?
That's your problem,
you're a liar.
I'm a liar?
She lied earlier about even
telling you about our bet.
I don't even know
why you're trying to like...
- Exactly.
- ...get in our business.
- I don't care about
your thing, my point is...
- Sit down, sit down.
My point is, I don't have time
for people to come,
in my atmosphere...
- I think... I think...
- ...with lies and...
You know what, Ryan.
Ryan... no.
Then go home bro,
I'm done with this.
You're calling her a liar,
bro, why are you being
so rude to her.
- Yeah, you're...
- 'Cause you just lied
about what you said.
- You know what...
- Why are you being
so rude to her?
- ...you need...
- Don't be rude to her.
I like Stefany, like,
don't talk to my girl
like that.
I definitely think Ryan
ruined his chance
with Stefany acting like that.
I think she wants
a mature guy.
[clicks tongue]
I think your feelings are hurt
because she doesn't like you.
Then why did she kissed me
on the beach,
telling me that she doesn't
[bleep] would you want
to [bleep] me.
[Stefany] You know what,
you're so narcissistic.
Yeah, I had a... yeah. Yeah.
[Ryan] And when the lie
comes out,
then that's what we do.
I hate all of this drama,
we went on one date,
I kissed him
one time, that's it.
I think Gabriel and I have
a really strong connection,
and that's
what's most important.
Ryan,
you are so disrespectful.
You... you channeled this.
You're a liar,
and that's bogus.
You 45 years,
you are too old
to be doing it.
- Okay, now I'm too old
to be dealing with this.
- No, no, you...
so you're going to walk out
with 23-year-old that
you just said...
- My room's upstairs.
- Get out of here bro.
[Stefany] He is crazy.
I know, I'm coming
straight like that
because it's ridiculous.
- He's so crazy.
- It's ridiculous.
I lied to him,
okay, whatever.
His... his feelings are hurt.
[Stefany] Yeah.
At this point,
I'm over it, but I just know
what works for me
and what doesn't work for me.
And Stefany
doesn't work for me.
How good are you
with your hands,
it's time for the woman
to judge that.
[Lisa] Yes.
Oh, perfect pressure.
There's nothing hotter,
to be massaged
by eight young men.
[groans]
I think I'm massaging
my mom's back.
That's it, right there baby.
I kind of want
to throw up a little bit.
From your standpoint,
like, what turned you on
about women?
Hmm, let's see
what turns me on the most.
I'm gonna be real,
I'm a little nervous,
because Charlene's
a little bit aggressive.
- I like to, you know...
- Yeah.
I've never experienced
something like this.
I have a plan for tonight,
but we would have
to sneak out.
[Kelle] I know that Jose
has been dating a lot of women
in the house, but tonight
I'm going to show him
that I'm the one
he should be with.