Previously on MILF Manor,
The time has come to see
if you've found a match.
If your choice is a mismatch,
you will be leaving
the villa today.
Wow.
We need to select,
who we have the strongest
connection with.
With the hopes that,
that person feels the same.
Oh, boy.
Congratulations, you and
Stephany chose each other.
Yay!
You and April chose
each other.
I needed to make a decision
but it wasn't easy.
Ryan, I chose you.
The woman that I chose
is Kelle.
[Pola] I really cannot
believe Jose chose Kelle.
And I'm not happy with that.
I don't see them together
outside The Villa.
Down to us.
Yeah, that's everyone.
Let's see what your friends
and family have to say
about your new relationship.
Is this seat taken?
[both screaming]
I think it's a very big deal
that Jose and my sister
get along.
Because if they don't--
If Mckenna doesn't like Jose,
he out.
How far has your
intimacy gone?
Mckenna is definitely
someone with a very strong personality.
So similar to Kelle and...
some of Mckenna's questions
makes me question if Kelle is
a match for me or not.
[all laughing]
Emma!
My only concern about
my daughter Emma, is not
liking Ryan.
She's not easy.
Do you want children?
One day, I'd be open to it.
Because my mother doesn't want
any more children.
- Oh, my Lord!
- Come here, Baby doll.
- What are you doing?
- How are you?
It's so good to see you.
Enough, come home.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
- What's happening?
- I'm taking her.
Is this guy actually serious?
Like, is this... Am I being
pranked right now?
So, you're really cute.
Thank you, thank you.
- You are.
- You are too.
How serious, you are with
your date?
I'm a little hurt about what happened
earlier today with April.
Emma showing up definitely
changes the game.
And I'm starting to wonder if
April is the right one for me.
Will you be down to know me?
[Emma] All right,
are we gonna play truth
or dare?
[April] Your call.
You're our guest.
[Jose] Truth or dare is not
one of my favorite games because
you need to be open
to doing things that
you're not necessarily do.
Having my sister and my mom
and the woman I'm dating and
the guy that my mom is dating
and Kelle's daughter and son and
I don't know, this could get
out of control really quickly.
And I don't like that.
Okay.
- [Kelle] Emma.
- Oh, god.
Truth or dare, darling?
Truth.
Oh, you want truth?
- Yeah sure.
- I love a good truth.
- When you saw, Joey, truthfully,
- Mm-hmm
what did you feel
when you saw him?
You want the truth?
Um, I love that Emma
has shown up.
Because it's gonna put April
to the test.
Because she needs
to step it up or step out.
Because to know how April's ex
treated him, like, maybe you
don't need to be around that.
So, I'm definitely looking out
for Joey.
You know, when you were, like,
everyone, like when they were young
I'm saying, I'm saying, like,
when you were 10 years-old,
9 years-old, you know,
then you meet a boy or a girl,
and you just feel, like, butterflies.
It did happen.
And it's cool to feel that,
you know.
[April] You know I did think
it was little bold of Emma
to say,
she has butterflies in front
of me.
Since she probably knows
what's going on with
Joey and I,
that we've had this connection.
Just because Joey and Emma
are around the similar age,
doesn't mean that outweighs
all the time I've spent with Joey.
Building something meaningful
that could lead to more.
Next dare it's
you.
Dare.
Do a body shot off Jose.
Oh, no problem.
Jose all you need to do
is take your shirt off
and lay down.
It's your sister.
- That's all you need to do
- Why you acting so scared?
You live in Miami, come on.
Does that face look,
like, scared?
[people cheering]
Praise the Lord. I was just
praying somebody would
tell me to do that.
I think he was more scared
of you.
Scared? I wasn't scared.
No, thanks, Emma.
I slid her a 100 bucks.
Suck it off his nipple.
Oh, geez.
[Mckenna] Suck that tequila
up, let's go.
[people laughing and teasing]
[Mckenna] Get it mommy.
[laughs]
[Emma] You want more?
[Pola] I was watching
but I was not watching.
I was there but I wasn't there so...
It's pretty weird.
Kelle was so happy about it.
I mean it's not fun
My turn.
April,
truth or dare?
[April] Um,
Dare.
[all exclaiming]
I dare you to give Joey
a kiss.
I used to be really jealous
when I was younger.
And I see Joey sitting next
to Emma.
And
I was feeling
a little uncomfortable.
But then I just remembered
who I am.
I'm confident that we have
something strong.
Move ladies.
He's getting all the,
all the women tonight.
[all chuckling]
Wow, it's like a whole scene.
[April] Okay.
That's cute. That was cute.
I am a little surprised that
Jose dared April to kiss you.
But she's, uh, putting Emma
in check, like, "This is my
man girl,
you need to back off."
I like you Joey.
[Joey] I mean as good
as that kiss was,
I just can't get over the way
April's ex Billy was treating
me. But also,
I'm starting
to, you know, get feelings
for Emma a little bit.
So, I don't know,
I'm conflicted.
So, we definitely gotta
have a talk.
So, what do you think
of my son with, beautiful
Stefany?
I see that your son
is precious.
He's so respectful.
You've done a great
job raising him.
[hesitates] Excuse me.
Oh, hi.
This is Joey, Mckenna's son.
I'm Joey, nice to meet you.
- He's the younger one.
- You are so beautiful.
- So beautiful.
- Thank you.
And he's my honey.
Mhm
But if I could please excuse
you women so I could talk
to April one on one,
I'm so sorry.
[Both] Okay.
Me and April need to have
a talk after
what her ex did at lunch.
Because the way that he picked
her up made it look like they
still had stuff going on.
And then, with Emma saying
she likes me now, and that
kiss with April,
I just need to get some
clarity on the situation
to see if April takes me
as seriously as I'm taking her.
I wanted to talk to you about
how our lunch date went.
When Billy came in I was
so excited to meet him.
And I feel like when he sat
down he kind of gave me, you
know, the cold shoulder.
Kind of turn away from me and
just look at you
and I get he hasn't seen you
in such a long time.
But at least like give me
a chance
- I understand, yeah.
- to say something.
I understand.
And when he took you away,
I kind of felt, like,
disrespected in a way
because--
- You know, when he did that,
it's just his personality.
- Yeah, yeah.
He's just, like,
whoom, before I knew it,
I'm just like where are we
going? What's happening?
But it kind of just left me
in the dust.
[April] The last thing I ever
wanna do is
have Joey feel disrespected.
Billy has a sense of humor.
And people may not understand
his personality until they get
to know him.
But I would never wanna hurt
Joey's feelings.
- So, mhm.
- So, here's the thing,
- you're 20 and...
- Mhmm
- He's my ex-husband,
he's the father of my kids.
- Mhm
I don't think he knew exactly
what was going on, you know,
I mean,
I didn't explain to him that
you and I connected.
But I didn't mean for,
you know to leave you out
in any way.
If there's a chance that
you guys will talk,
and he's a super cool guy,
very talented.
Yeah, but if he's not
acknowledging me then
- why waste my energy,
trying to,
- I hear you
you know, acknowledge him.
Even though Billy and April
are divorced, I would
definitely say that
they're a lot closer than
what she's been telling me.
So, I'm not sure what
to think.
I'm annoyed that she's
not really siding with me.
Because she knows the way
he was acting was just wrong.
It definitely makes me
question whether
the chemistry and bond that
we've had is as real as
it felt.
He is a very good person with
a huge heart.
And I would love to see that.
He didn't care to get to know
me at all.
So,
really in my opinion, I,
excuse my language
but I could give a [bleep]
to get to know him
- Okay, okay.
- at all.
You are nearing the
end of your time here
at the villa.
No!
And some of you have already
spent your last night here.
[Ryan] Wait what?
What do you think of Jose?
I think he's amazing.
I think he's a very special person.
I loved meeting his mom
Pola, I loved meeting
Emma his sister.
I love that their very family oriented.
And I loved seeing
your connection.
So, how do you [hesitates]
feel?
- I honestly adore him.
- Mhm
Because I feel like I know
him deeper than what you get
to see here in, like, in day.
You deserve the best
of the best.
You deserve everything that
you want.
I think you need romance.
I know you want that.
And if you have any
reservations about romance
with somebody, I think,
take it day by day, do your
thing, have so much fun.
We're almost done. Wow.
- With the best time.
- You're beautiful [indistinct]
If not I go home with you.
[McKenna] There's just
a little skepticism from me because
I don't think they've had
enough quality time together.
Which knowing my mom,
she needs that quality time
and she needs more
physicality, like, someone
who's very assertive.
And, you know, pin me
against the wall, let me
see the passion.
Um, I don't see that between them.
So, without having that,
it made me a little nervous.
[Both] I love you so much.
[Emma] Hello.
Hello, Emma.
- How are you doing?
- I'm good.
- Mhm
- About to leave tomorrow.
- Really?
- Yeah, I'm headed
back home.
- I mean that's really
sad but--
- But
- I wanted to ask you something.
- Mhm
- I know that you're in LA and
I'm in Miami but...
- Mhm
maybe if I go to LA or you
come to Miami do you want,
can I have your phone?
I'm very conflicted because I
don't know if I wanna go with
April or Ms. Emma.
I mean, they're both
great people.
I still don't know Emma
as much but
I'm definitely not 100%
certain that April's got
the same feelings for me.
What do you want
my name under?
- Really?
- Yeah, I'm headed
back home.
I'm definitely keeping my
options open
because I don't know what
to expect from April anymore.
- So, I have your phone number.
- Mhm.
Oh, you got it now.
- I'm gonna text you,
you better answer.
- Yeah.
Later Emma.
Bye.
[phone chimes]
I have a text.
- We got a text.
- Yes!
- [Joey] Get comfortable.
- Oh, boy.
Couples, you are nearing
the end of your time here
at the villa.
No!
Some of you have already spent
your last night here.
[Ryan] Wait what?
You'll each write a letter
to your partner,
stating your intentions.
And if you would like this
relationship to continue
outside the villa.
Tomorrow you will read your
letters to each other.
Will you stay together
or go your separate ways?
Only time will tell.
it's so sad.
Men, you will now leave
the villa to write your
letters in private.
Ladies, you will stay here
till tomorrow.
What does it mean continue
outside the villa, like?
- Yeah I know.
- Like in the future having a
relationship with that person.
[April] I don't like
this text.
I wasn't expecting that.
Knowing that this potentially
could just be the end
It's a little nerve wracking.
I definitely will be
heartbroken if I don't
see Gabriel again.
This is a lot to digest.
I'm actually really sad that
this is almost over.
I love spending time
with Jose.
And now we have to write
a letter to say how we feel.
And I think it's gonna be very
hard for me because he's just
such a special man.
I'm going to miss everyone.
I feel like we were all, like,
kind of stunned.
Me and the guys
we're all like,
"Damn, like, this is it,
we need to make a decision."
I just feel like it's kind of
abrupt and we're all like...
Kind of scared, so I'm
nervous, I'm nervy right now.
Wow.
[Jose] The men in the house
have spent the last night
at the villa.
So, this sparks a lot of mixed
feelings because
outside of this villa it
becomes more real because
we have to align our lives.
And to overcome a 1000 other
obstacles we didn't have before.
So, it's very difficult
to face it.
Wow, it's only us four ladies
left in this house.
I have separation anxiety already.
That's kinda scary.
I wasn't expecting that
- Me either.
- at all.
I don't think it was a good
choice for Jose to choose Kelle.
So, I hope this time he
chooses not to be with her.
Maybe it's gonna be the end
of that relationship.
[Kelle] I'm really emotional
writing this letter to Jose
right now because,
I realized it was time
to say goodbye.
I am dying right now.
You know my heart.
Thank you for being
so damn amazing.
Ahh,
Do you think there is a chance
for us to be a couple when we
get back to LA?
I remember our first conversation.
I'm writing a letter
whether or not we should either
continue our relationship when
we go back home or we should
just keep it as friends.
I feel like even though we've
had plenty of conversations
we haven't gotten down
to the nitty gritty at all.
What does he want for
his life?
Does he wanna have kids?
I have kids.
My kids are in their 20s.
So, there's a lot we've just
scratched the surface with.
And I am worried that,
you know, our gap as far
as our age range,
is quite something and...
I don't wanna rob anyone
of their life experience.
So,
I don't really know what
to do right now. I have
to figure it out.
It's not my cup of tea but
I guess we'll give it a try.
"Dear April,
the girl that I've always,,,"
[sighs wearily]
I'm a terrible writer.
So, this is gonna
be very difficult.
Yeah, I mean my mind
is racing.
The doubts are definitely
there whether, you know,
I wanna have a relationship
with April
or whether she wants to have
a relationship with me.
After everything that's gone
on with her ex,
I don't know what to do.
"This amazing time,
this journey,
this experience."
Exper... How do you spell
experience? Oh, I can't
do this.
So difficult.
I'm actually a little nervous
to really put my thoughts
on paper.
I don't think I've ever
written a letter to any guy.
But, you know, Gabriel
is someone special to me.
I'm being very vulnerable.
I'm putting everything out
there, you know, and just
take this by faith.
And see what God's plan
is for me at the end.
I am definitely ready
to be with somebody serious.
I am looking for a partner.
I wanna get married again.
So, you know, I'm hoping that
he could be ready for some
commitment here.
[Gabriel] As I'm writing this letter,
a 1000 thoughts at a 1000
miles per hour is going
through my head and
I know what I like about
Stefany and it is
her genuineness, her sexiness,
how strong and independent
she is and that's my type.
But I'm thinking about how she
has a whole family already.
I personally, you know,
always wanted kids.
I'm thinking about
my lifestyle.
I travel a lot, if I even have time
for something so serious.
Eh, it's just,
it's uncomfortable.
My dear Ryan,
For me it is really difficult
to start a letter because
I wanna be sincere,
I wanna be clear.
But I'm not really clear, my
mind is not clear because
I don't know what's going on.
After I leave the villa...
It was the way you made
me laugh.
Being around Ryan, everything
is really fun.
So I have a very good time
being around him.
But he lives in Boston I live
in Miami
so I don't know if this
connection will stay as
strong as it is right now.
And that scares me because
I don't know if there's gonna
be a future or not.
Dear Pola
As I write my letter, I'm
using this time to look into
my feelings for Pola.
And potentially where I can
see this thing really taking
off to.
I started a song,
♪ You ain't gotta hide your
imperfections ♪
♪ I think they sexy ♪
This song is unfinished,
because it's a story that
I don't want to end.
That's how I feel about Pola.
That's how I feel about
the time we spent together
in this villa.
I think I did find love here.
And that's not something that
I'm ready to let go.
I'm going to put my heart,
my soul,
all over this letter
And I'm ready to merge
our two worlds.
I'm going all in.
[Jose] Writing this letter
is a roller-coaster
of emotions,
I have very special connection
with Kelle,
and we know how we feel
about each other.
But, there are many factors
we need to consider
in order to align our lives,
which makes me question,
if, it's a match for me...
or not.
[Kelle] I'm really emotional
Writing this letter
to Jose right now because,
I feel like,
I can finally really tell him
how I've been feeling
the whole time
since I met him.
It's like ridiculous,
how fast
someone can impact your life.
[sobs] I don't get it.
For the first time,
I feel like, I really have
connected with somebody
who gets me
and actually has my back
When you talk to--
[voice shaking]
[sniffles]
And, um,
I really just don't wanna
say goodbye.
[sobs] I am dying right now
[sighs, sniffles]
[sniffles]
[Shannan] I have been on pins
and needles about coming back
to the final ceremony.
I have no idea what to expect.
I'm hopin'
and I'm praying that,
you know,
this pans out.
For Pola and Ryan.
That was the purpose
of me coming
to this retreat...
to find love.
So, that's all I want for him.
Well, this is excitin'.
- This is it, right?
- Yeah.
[Jimmy] You know we've made
some great connections,
and we just wish the best
for everybody,
- you know.
- Yeah, I wanna see
how they turned out.
- if they find their real love.
- Right?
[Kelle] It's very exciting
to see,
that everyone's
back here at the villa,
to support us
in this very last moment.
I'm definitely very nervous.
Knowing that I'm crying
writing the letter,
now I had to read it
in front of 'em.
Like, am I gonna
break down crying? [chuckles]
But, I'm excited
to share with him
how I really feel.
[April] Here we are.
Our journey's
coming to an end.
And, it's very bitter-sweet.
Just, it's time for me
to tell him how I feel and...
I just hope
we're both on the same page.
The energy right now
is really intense.
Everybody's looking at me.
And everybody knows
that it's in my hands
to make a decision.
[Stefany] It's been a while
since I felt like this
about someone.
I've no idea what Gabriel
is feeling right now,
but I'm definitely anxious
to know,
exactly where his mind
or heart is.
Hey.
Aw, nice stud.
Look at you.
Man, so this is it.
Crazy.
Here it goes.
[chuckles nervously]
Hopefully I don't cry.
[smacks lips]
So, dear Gabriel,
I never imagined
that I can open up
to a man of such young age
as I have with you.
Comin' into the villa,
I had no idea
who I was going to meet,
or how this experiment
was going to play out.
[chuckles]
[sniffles] However,
you were the guy
that always stood out to me.
- [smacks lips]
- [choking up]
Your confidence...
- [voice shaking]
I'm gonna cry.
- Don't cry.
your energy,
and the love you show
to your mom daily,
was amazingly sweet.
They say, a man that has
a great relationship
with his mom,
is a man that you must keep.
[sniffles] I will forever
be grateful,
and cherish every moment
we spent together,
here at the villa.
I don't know
what to call our relationship
once we leave the villa.
But, I want it to be
as deep and loving,
as it is for me today.
Thank you for being
so damn amazing.
[chuckles]
- Ah!
- [sniffles]
[chuckles]
My mom has genuine feelings
towards Gabriel.
[Pola] Aw!
- [crowd clapping]
- So, I'm definitely interested
to see how Gabriel feels,
I think my mom
would definitely be hurt
if Gabriel had said,
the feeling wasn't mutual.
I think she would be upset
it wasn't the result
she wanted.
Dear Stefany,
day one, I immediately wanted
to get to know you.
When I first saw you
by the bar outside,
I was struck by your energy,
and beauty.
- [paper rustles]
- [chuckles]
After our first date,
I knew that I wouldn't want to
spend this journey
with anyone else.
You challenge me
in such a way,
that made me wanna
take my time to build
a genuine connection.
- [paper rustles]
- I wanted to be creative,
and go all in to prove
- how special you truly are.
- [paper rustles]
You deserve the best.
I thank you so much for this.
With love, Gabriel Jane.
[Stefany] I am nervous.
I have anxiety...
because Gabriel's letter...
it's coming across like,
he is not ready to commit.
I have no idea
where this is going.
I hope,
this is not the end of us.
[waves splashing]
So, do you think
there's a chance
for us to be a couple,
when we get back to LA?
[exhales]
[waves splashing]
So, do you think
there's a chance
for us to be a couple,
when we get back to LA?
[April] I feel like,
in the real world,
Gabriel and Stefany
may not work.
because Gabriel
is constantly travelling,
and working
and he has so much more
to see and to learn,
as a young man.
And, Stefany is more settled,
and she wants somebody
more stable
and, Gabriel's
just not here yet.
Of course, I'm excited
for our future adventures,
and I can't wait
to get back to LA and...
and give you
a taste of my lifestyle.
Okay.
I was scared of taking it
to that next level.
But, I realized,
that someone
I would wanna be
in a relationship with,
would be someone,
I could be best friends with.
And, I feel like,
Stefany and I, have that.
[Stefany laughing]
I'm excited that I was blessed
to meet this amazing man,
and, I'm gonna take him
to my church,
- Yes. We're gonna have
lots of f--
- I'll burn up.
[both laugh]
Mmm... Ah...
- Joey.
- [crowd claps, hoots]
[Joey] I wrote down
my feelings on a page.
So, I'm feeling
a lot of pressure
reading this.
Looking beautiful.
I mean, I'm nervous
about April's response.
But,
I'm also hopeful because,
I really got a feeling
that she feels the same way.
Dear April,
the second I saw you,
my eyes lit up
like a Christmas tree.
[chuckles]
From our very first conversation,
I started a bond with you,
and my mind was completely
open into areas,
I didn't know I had.
You unlocked me.
[chuckling]
You proved to me
that age is just a number
on your driver's license.
[clicks tongue]
That's right, baby.
[Joey] Mmm-hmm.
You have truly
changed my life forever.
Aw!
Without meeting you,
I would never be able to see
my true potential.
Within myself,
or as you would like
to call me,
[chuckles] an old soul.
That's right.
You taught me
the art of happiness,
how to communicate,
and most importantly,
how to show and receive love,
to the person
you care about most.
To something [indistinct]
April,
I'm so glad I met you.
And I would love
to continue dating
outside of the building.
[April speaking, laughing]
[crowd hooting]
[all laughing]
[April] I feel flattered,
that Joey would want
to date me
outside of the villa.
in the real world.
That must mean
that he really sees me
for who I am.
And, it makes me realize
that he does care about me,
as a person.
Dear Joey,
Even though you are only 20,
you have it together.
[inaudible]
- Mmm.
- You said that you saw
a light around me,
and a halo over my h--
[voice shaking, sobs]
[sniffles]
[sobs, sniffles]
- [Joey whispers] It's okay.
- [sniffles]
[sobbing, sniffling]
That meant so much to me.
I sincerely have nothing
but good to say about you, Joey.
Thank you, sweet Joey.
And I love you lots.
- Mmm.
- Let's continue
growing together,
and help each other
along our journeys
through life.
And one more thing, Joey.
As a 20 year old man,
I'm sure this will appeal
to you.
You are free, Joey.
Free to be close to me...
and close to someone else.
If, for example,
You would like to see
where things go with Emma,
- and where they go
from there...
- Mmm...
[exhales]
- [April speaking]
- I know.
[April and Joey
speaking softly]
I feel like,
it was the right move,
for my mom and Joey
to just be friends.
I feel like,
my mom's not really
ready to be so romantic,
specially with
such a young man
If anything,
I feel a little bad for Joey.
I hope Joey
doesn't take it too rough.
I'm a little hurt,
the way April let me down
on her letter.
I can't wait to take them home
- and put it in my drawer
forever. [chuckles]
- Aw, no.
But, you know, life goes on,
and hey...
you get shot down,
you get back up and...
I really do hope
to find someone
with a soul connection
Could be Emma,
could be someone
five years down that road.
I mean, I just never know.
Oh, my God.
[Joey] So much.
[April] I know, right?
We're leaving the villa as...
[both] BFFs.
Wow, wow!
Your feet look like
they're dying in those heels.
- Ugh, it's terrible.
- [Joey grunts]
[April screams]
[both laugh]
[sighs]
[Ryan] Walkin' up,
to present this letter,
feels like judgement day.
Oh!
I feel like I've put
a lot into this,
and this is, um,
this is new for me.
- How are you?
- Very good and you?
- [Ryan] You look amazin'
as usual.
- I missed you.
I missed you too.
[kisses]
I want my yes, you know.
I want my yes.
I'm feelin' like...
If Pola shuts me down
and she doesn't wanna build
outside of these walls,
I am going to be crushed.
Dear Pola,
you are truly
one of the most amazing women,
that I've met in my lifetime.
As our story continues,
I will continue to deliver
and add to every chapter,
as promised.
With unmatched style,
grace, excellence,
and humility,
I see the love that
you are capable of giving.
Culturally, we are different.
but our hearts are the same.
You don't have to hide
your imperfections.
- [chuckles]
- I think they're sexy.
- You can be vulnerable,
with me, baby.
I am your protection.
Now...
[laughs]
as promised.
This verse to your song,
is unfinished.
Like the business
that I have with you.
I invite you to continue,
creating with me,
one baby step at a time.
After listening
to what he told me,
in his letter,
I am really clear about
how I feel about him
and it's in my hands
to make a decision.
- But, I feel scared...
- [paper rustles]
[speaking foreign language Ryan,
My dear, Ryan.
I can't even begin to express,
the emotions
that are currently running
through my head,
my heart,
and everyone in between.
There have been moments
in my life,
where I have been absent
and just went through
the emotions,
In this case,
I was able to be present
[sniffles]
every moment I experienced
with you.
While we explore
other possibilities,
we were still looking
for each other's company.
That's when I realized,
I shouldn't be afraid
and just go for it.
Thank you for my song.
[sniffles] And let our future
decide the last words
of the song.
- [Ryan] Okay.
- Of our song.
So, what I'm saying,
to be clear is...
[sniffles]
Every story has a beginning...
a middle, and an end.
Or a continuance,
in this case,
I believe, there is room
for more chapters
to be written.
Like coming to Miami will too.
[Ryan yells] Hey!
I will come to Miami.
[both laughing]
[crowd hooting]
I'm ecstatic
for Pola and Ryan.
I am so happy that
she followed her heart.
Long term,
I do see great potential,
for Ryan and Pola.
[Pola] You surprised me.
That letter was amazing.
I couldn't handle it.
It was beautiful.
Good good.
I love to surprise you.
You always do.
I'm excited about
takin' our relationship
to the next level.
It's somethin'
I'm lookin' forward to.
Yes. The next step is
no kids, no moms.
The next step,
no kids--
- No kids, no moms.
- no m-- unless you want
some more kids.
- No, no, no, no.
- You want some--
- I'm fine with two.
- [both laughing]
[Kelle] While I'm standing
there, waiting for Jose
to walk up the stairs.
I'm like, oh, my God.
Please don't dump me.
Ugh!
[crowd hooting, clapping]
Wow.
Are you nervous?
Very.
It's okay.
[Jose] I'm feeling
very anxious.
I know what my decision is
about Kelle.
I just don't wanna
disappoint her.
- Look good.
- You look amazing.
Thanks, so do you.
[Jose] I'm ready to tell Kelle
how I feel.
I don't know how well
or bad it can go.
Uh... [sighs]
From the first time I saw you,
I was like,
wow!
And you just did it again.
Then, when we first spoke,
I thought you weren't real
because you seemed to be
too perfect.
When you talk to people,
I can tell you listen
to everything they say.
[sniffles] And that's when
I knew, you were really
something special.
When you accepted
our first date,
it made me so nervous,
yet so excited.
I remember you saying,
you take things very slow.
So, I decided, back off.
Then I waited patiently
hoping that if we had
some more time together.
- [Kelle sniffles]
- [paper rustles]
We could see if this could
blossom into something more.
I know we have distance
between us.
But I'm willing
to make that effort.
to keep this connection going,
to see where it goes.
So, Jose,
it's an easy decision for me.
to want to spend
more and more time with you.
I wanna lift you up,
empower you and cheer you on,
into becoming the man
that you were created to be.
Love, Kelle a.k.a Disco Mommy.
[both chuckle]
- Thank you.
- Mmm-hmm.
Hearing how she's expressing
herself about me,
generates a lot of pressure,
in terms of the expectation
that she has,
from what I have to say.
And I'm nervous about it.
Now it's my turn.
Oh, God.
Dear Kelle,
there are so many things
that I wanna say.
You are a bright, brave
and admirable woman.
So full of energy and life.
I know we have both enjoyed
each moment each day,
[paper rustles]
Oh!
I'm nervous for my mom.
I'm just really hoping that
Jose feels the same way
that my mom does.
As this part of our adventure
comes to an end,
I am hopeful
we will have new ones,
to look forward to,
together.
Yours truly, Jose.
Aw!
[crowd clapping]
[Pola] I'm a little bit disappointed,
but, Jose has something
with Kelle.
He feels good around her.
So, at the beginning
it was really difficult
to know Kelle
and maybe I misunderstood her.
But at this moment,
I see her intentions
and she has good intentions
with Jose.
So, I need to give them
a chance.
When can you come to LA?
Is tomorrow too soon?
[both laugh]
[Joey] I'm ecstatic for my mom
and Jose,
because,
she really deserves someone,
who knows how to handle
all of her energy,
and is on the same wavelength
as her,
when it comes to giving love
and receiving love.
[all cheering]
Get up, get up.
[Jose] Today was
a very special day.
We both had an opportunity
to express our feelings
to each other and I think,
- it went great.
- [Kelle chuckles]
[Joey] My God!
[Jose] In this house we found
something magical.
[Kelle] I was hoping
from day one,
I would be with him...
the whole time.
[Jose] Mmm.
- How's it been?
- It's good to see you.
- You too.
- [crowd speaking indistinctly]
You look happy.
- [both laugh]
- [Shannan] I would say,
this experience with him,
has definitely
taken our relationship
to another level.
Um, it has helped me
appreciate him,
as a young man,
not just my son.
Uh, I've got to learn somethings,
probably way more
than I needed to learn.
[both laugh]
But, nonetheless,
if I had to do it all
over again,
I would.
It was a special time.
[crowd speaking indistinctly]
Wow, what a journey!
[Billy] Yeah! We did it!
- [Stefany] I know!
- [Billy] We did it.
[Stefany] I think
this experience
has made us, um,
you know, realize that,
hey have fun,
and you know,
age is just a number.
Definitely,
keep your options open.
and only God would,
you know, guide you,
to make the right decision.
[Kelle] You really did embrace
every moment of this journey.
Even though there were so many
twists and turns,
and things that were
completely unexpected.
You took everything, like,
with a grain of salt.
and I'm very proud of you.
I wouldn't wanna do it
with anyone else.
Thanks, Mom.
Even though she's known me
my whole life,
we still learn things that
we've never known
about each other.
One thing I learned about you is...
the bathroom is always a mess
with all your make up.
But, I still love you.
That's it?
That's all you learned?
Yeah. I already know
everything about you.
- Oh!
- I knew you were gonna be crazy...
in a good way.
- We found a family here.
- [women] Yes.
Like, more than anything,
like. you guys are so special,
- every single one of you.
I love you guys.
- Cheers!
We learned that
there's happiness
and there's love to be found.
and only that,
that we are not obstacles,
in each other's love life.
which is very nice.
[Pola speaking]
And, that's something
I didn't understand
until I did this.
- and was part of this
wonderful experience.
- Yeah.
- To our mothers.
- [crowd] Cheers!
- And to the sons.
- Our babies.
- [yells] To the villa.
To the villa.
- [all cheering]
[all] Cheers!
[glasses clinking]