My name is April Jane,
and I am in my 50s.
I'm a vintage, rare find.
I live in Studio City,
California,
and I have three
amazing boys.
I don't think
any of my sons realize
that I have
an extremely high libido.
Hold on.
Is that too much saying
I have an extremely
high libido?
Should I just have said
My marriage was wonderful
for a while.
We got together
when we were very young.
I am seven years
older than him.
We just realized that
we weren't completely
compatible.
I thought I had
my whole life planned,
but now I'm here,
open to the adventure.
I'm open to having
a connection
with another younger man.
I hope I'm really gonna
find love.
[sighs]
[Pola] My name is Pola.
I am originally
from Mexico City,
but right now I live in Miami,
in a paradise.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
My name is Pola.
Nice to meet you.
Hi, Pola.
Nice to meet you, too. April.
[Pola] April.
Nice to meet you. Pleasure.
I'm expecting
for some guys to walk up
and introduce themselves.
And here comes Pola.
And it surprised me.
- Nice to meet you, Pola.
- [Pola] Welcome to Mexico.
Thank you.
I'm not necessarily
a competitive person,
but I'm confident,
and she doesn't have
anything on me.
- [Pola] Where are you from?
- I'm from Los Angeles.
- [Pola] Oh, that's nice.
- Such pretty eyes.
- You like Mexico?
- I love it.
- It's beautiful, right?
- It's gorgeous.
- Yes.
- It is gorgeous.
When I was 23 years old,
my husband passed away
in a car accident.
It was really hard,
but I wanted a good life
for my kids,
so I decided I was gonna
live my life happily,
make good memories
with my kids,
and just move forward.
- Salud.
I'm totally ready
to take that risk
and find that special guy.
I'm that kind of woman
that really likes
to be around a man.
I've never been by myself.
Like, in kindergarten,
I had boyfriends.
Like, I've always been
around someone special.
So if someone proposed
while I'm here,
that would be great news.
I don't know what...
if it's gonna happen or not,
but let's see.
So what do you do in LA?
- I'm a singer.
- Oh, really?
Can I ask you your age?
- No, you can't. No.
- [laughs]
My name is Soyoung.
I am 50 years old.
When I meet good-looking,
my type of a man,
I'll introduce myself and say,
"Hey, I'm Soyoung
and I'm so [bleep]."
- [Pola] Hi.
- How are you?
Hey! How are you?
[April Jane] Good.
How are you?
- [Pola] Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
I'm Soyoung.
- [April Jane] Soyoung?
- Yes.
I always dated a young guy.
My second husband
was younger.
All my boyfriends was young.
Always ten years younger.
I'm a fire love.
I have to have those fire,
love to have sex.
If I don't have that,
I could have sex,
but I can't kiss anybody
because that's disgusting.
[April Jane]
Where are you from?
I'm originally
from South Korea.
- [April Jane] Oh, are you?
- Yeah.
- [Pola] Oh, I love--
- [April Jane] Nice.
How old were you
when you moved out?
How many years ago
did you move to--
That's when I was 19,
18 and a half. So yeah.
- Adventurous.
- Yeah, I am.
Like, I'm not afraid
of things, like anything.
How about of this?
Yes. Just like this.
[chuckles]
[Pola] Soyoung is cute.
I'm sure
she's gonna get picked
with many other guys,
but if she likes
the same guy that I do like,
I will be competitive. And...
[Pola speaking]
I don't care about
any other thing.
I want to win.
We're gonna start the day.
- Nice meeting you.
- Yay!
- Nice to meet you.
- Woo-hoo!
My name is April.
I'm 43 years old.
I'm from Detroit, Michigan.
I'm a very simple girl.
I married
my high school sweetheart.
I met him at 14.
We had our children together
and we were married
for 14 years.
So that has been my really
longest relationship.
- [April] Hi!
- [Pola] Hola.
[April]
You guys look so pretty.
- I'm April.
- April, I'm April.
- There's two Aprils.
- [laughter]
Right.
I gave a lot of my youth
to raising my boys.
Now, at 43, I'm just looking
to have fun.
And I want
to date younger men
because a lot of guys
that are older,
they're like in "papa mode",
and I want to get a chance
to do me a little.
So when it's time for me
to be grandma, like I'm ready.
I'm just not ready now.
Ladies,
where's all the men at?
Are you kidding me?
You guys look great.
Hi.
My name is Charlene.
I'm from Jersey,
but currently I live in
Los Angeles, Hollywood.
- Hi.
- [April] What did you say
your name was again?
- Charlene.
- Charlene. Right.
Yeah. I think it's my time
to find love.
I really do.
Because life has,
you know, really given me
some curveballs,
and it took a long time
to get here.
It's so nice to meet
new people, so, you know.
So I'm wearing
two necklaces today.
The first one
is an infinity necklace
that my daughter,
Ashley, got for me.
And she's my oldest daughter.
She would be 28 right now.
She just had her birthday,
but she passed away
when she was 27.
So it's not even been
a year yet.
Losing her was by far
the hardest thing
I've ever had to do,
and I'm doing it.
That's the thing.
I'm doing it.
My daughter was huge
in my life about dating.
She'd be the first person
I would talk to.
The first person I would ask.
[Charlene]
Are we looking for love,
are we looking for romance?
[April Jane]
I'm looking for love?
[Charlene]
I mean, look, it's like
love is in the air here.
- It's so...
- it's romantic.
It is romantic.
I am doing this for Ashley
in a lot of ways
because I think she wants me
to be happy.
I know she would want me
to be in love.
Like, hey, that's the hope.
Could I fall in love?
Could I get married
and come out of the dark like,
you know, a new chapter,
light on the horizon.
But it's been so long,
I don't know.
[Charlene]
I never know how...
how and why I'm gonna be
attracted to someone,
like their personality
to me, it can be more--
[Pola]
That's much more important.
[Charlene] Sometimes,
like really good-looking guys,
they're so...
- [April Jane]
They open their mouth...
- [Charlene] Yeah.
- Yeah,
I was gonna say that.
- [Charlene] It's not...
How about the guy
that are ugly and...
but he has a nice personality,
nice to you,
you're gonna date?
[Charlene] No,
no, no, no, no.
[April Jane] No,
I'm Kelle. I'm 50 years old,
and my alter ego
is Disco Mommy.
Hey, girls!
- [Pola] Hey!
- [Soyoung] Hello!
[Kelle] How are you
hot ladies doing?
Disco Mommy loves house music
and Disco Mommy,
she's really spontaneous.
She's just fun.
What can I get
you ladies to drink?
Do we need a shot?
[all laughing]
Kelle has a big personality.
Don't play with me.
I do think that, for me,
it's really too much.
She's just got to pare it back
just a little bit.
One, two, three, four.
All these women look amazingly
hot, but they're not me.
Always good vibes.
I have six amazing kids,
three girls and three boys,
and I feel like
I've been judged
by having multiple kids
from not having the same dad.
In fact, that's
the number one question
people ask me, like...
like, "From the same guy?"
I'm like, "No, why would
I have six kids
from the same guy?
Hello."
You're a bad influence
already, girl.
No, I'm an amazing influence
for sure.
[Shannan] Yeah, you are.
I think it's gonna be
a little bit hard to keep up
with Kelle.
She's gonna be the party girl
in this house.
- A good influence.
- To good influence.
Cheers, ladies. Go.
[Kelle] Well, I used to think
that age was an issue
until the first guy I dated
out of my marriage, right?
And he was like
14 years younger.
And then it became like
kind of a theme
that all these younger guys
I kept like hanging out
with and dating,
and we literally had
the best time.
And they taught me that,
you know,
they could be drawn
to an older woman.
And then I realized
I can teach younger men
a lot of things.
[producer speaking]
I don't know if I can say
that on TV.
[laughing]
[Shannan]
Were you married before?
I was married ten years.
[Shannan] So how is dating
going for you now?
Do younger guys gravitate
toward you?
- [Kelle] Yes.
- [Shannan]
Because you look so amazing.
- Yes. Thank you.
- [Shannan] Yeah. Yeah.
[April] Kelle is the most
risque of all the moms
with no shame whatsoever.
I'm not mad about my body.
[laughter]
[Charlene] I already feel
I'm the woman that will get
the least attention.
You could tell Kelle
has invested a lot of time
into her body,
her sex appeal.
And I know that
young men want that.
So she's got that
going for herself.
I have the best trainer
in Orange County,
- so if you guys want to come.
- Right.
[Charlene]
Everyone's very pretty
and I'm like
the biggest girl here.
Like, what do I have to offer?
[Charlene] You know,
we're getting older, ladies.
We're not getting younger,
even though we can think
that we can do things
to make ourselves look
younger, we're really not.
We're really not.
Marina Charlene is...
she probably was very hot
when she was younger,
um, more in shape.
I just feel like
she doesn't know
how to glam herself up.
I think she's just
a little worried about
not being pleasing
in that way to the guys.
I was asking them
what they do and then,
now I'm thinking we should
try to guess what you--
[April] Just guess
what you do.
- I feel like you do something
like with human resources.
- She's like corporate--
- Yes, I was just
gonna say that.
- Yeah. Yeah, right?
I plan corporate events
and meetings.
- You're an event planner?
- [Shannan] Yes.
I enjoy my work.
I have had the opportunity
to travel the world,
but I wasn't always
a corporate events planner.
I looked like the B-girl back
in the day
on the street corners
doing the break dance
and then the pop and lock
and on the cardboard.
So I like to have fun,
you know?
And I think
that most young men
could probably
appreciate that,
that I'm not stiff
and, you know,
or corny or prude.
Have you guys been dating
during COVID?
[Shannan]
Have you been dating?
- I haven't been.
- Not since.
[Stefany] Well, I'm open,
you know,
it's just
whatever God has, I guess.
- Amen to that.
- Right?
Whatever God's plan is.
It's actually really--
It's probably
why we're all here right now.
- [Stefany] Yes.
- Just seeing what's going on.
Exactly.
I've always been,
you know, a believer.
I love the Lord,
and I think it's important
with relationships.
I think your partner,
having God as the foundation
is very important.
You know, I feel like
a lot of older guys
don't want a commitment
because they're getting out
of a divorce.
- That is so funny.
- I was thinking
the same thing.
So they... they just want to
play the field a little bit.
And you're like,
"Yeah, it's time for--"
It's like, bro,
you're like 60.
Yeah. And you look like
you're 80, like come on.
And then you still want
to play the field?
Like, go, bye.
I am excited to see
what God has in store for me
and we'll see what happens
on this amazing journey.
I'm so thrilled.
[Stefany]
Wait, girls, hold on.
- I got a text. It says...
- Oh, yeah?
It says,
"Welcome to the villa.
You're about to embark
on a dating experience
like none other."
[all] Oh!
We all received phones so that
we could receive text messages
telling us what we're gonna do
in the villa.
I'm a little excited,
but also nervous
because we have no idea
what to expect.
"Please head to the house
where you will meet
the new men in your life."
- [cheering]
- [Stefany] Let's go.
- Vamanos.
- All right.
I'm so excited to meet
with these guys
because I know that these guys
are going to be younger.
I have a very young,
free spirit,
and I connect to younger men,
especially in the bedroom.
[Soyoung] All my life,
I've been looking for tall,
dark hair, blue eyes,
nice abs, thick thighs.
Hopefully he's here.
If not there,
out there anyone,
please call me, Soyoung.
[man 1] My special woman
has to be older,
and I'm here in Paradise
hoping to find my soulmate.
[man 2] I am so excited
to come on this retreat
and just meet
a ton of beautiful women
that are mature
and comfortable
with themselves.
[man 3] I love older women
that can keep up with me
because I'm bringing
that young energy.
I'm looking for love.
I need a grown woman
out here.
Let's go.
[Kelle] Here we go.
Here we go.
- Whoa!
- [Shannan] Yeah!
All right, now.
Grrr.
[Charlene] So curious
as to what I can find here.
I mean, this is it.
All of my moments
have led me to this one.
And hopefully
there is somebody here
that is gonna be
interested in me.
I could be
interested in them.
What's going on?
Wait. They're our moms?
Holy [bleep].
[April] Whoo!
That's my mom right there.
[Jose speaking
in foreign language]
[Pola speaking
Oh, my God!
I just saw straight
to Jose's eyes
and just stayed there
for a couple of seconds
and say, "What is this?"
I am really confused
right now.
What is really happening here?
[Harrison speaking]
[Charlene] I'm, like,
completely shocked.
I see my son
back there and it's like,
"Who are all these guys?"
[Billy] So[bleep] cool.
We're supposed to date
the other moms?
Uh...
And you're here.
That's so weird.
- Yeah.
- That is so weird.
[April Jane]
I knew my son Gabriel
was going to be
in Mexico with me.
I thought he was gonna be
on a separate dating retreat,
but he's in my dating pool.
And I'm gonna have to see
my son date these moms.
This is crazy, bro.
I'm feeling very overwhelmed
and a little scared.
Seeing my son standing
in that line
made me feel very awkward
because they're my son's age.
We're up. Let's go. We're up.
I was a little shocked
to see Ryan in the pool.
I didn't see that
coming at all.
[Ryan] I'm gonna be honest.
I'm thinking first pick
in the draft.
Like, I'm looking at
everything else before my mom.
Thank God for that.
[both laugh]
[Joey] Hi, Mom.
How are you doing?
[Kelle] Hey.
What are you doing here?
Why are you following me
on the retreat, Joey?
I'm here to find love.
Don't get in my way.
Honestly, honestly,
older women are very hot.
And I know I got the swag
and I got the game for them.
Wow. This is like news to me.
- Yes, Mom. Yes.
- Hmm.
I'm Joey.
Nice to meet you.
- Hey.
- What's your name?
- I'm April.
- April, nice to meet you.
- How are you?
- I'm doing great.
- How about you?
- I'm fine.
But whenever
I bring a woman home,
it's all up to my mom
whether I'm dating her or not.
Yes!
[Kelle speaking]
Been winning. Been winning.
- [Jose] Hi.
- Soyoung.
- How are you?
- So young.
- Oh, amazing.
- Soyoung.
Amazing, amazing, amazing.
[Pola speaking]
[laughter]
I think I have eye on,
uh, Jose.
He's a perfect age for me.
He don't have a tattoo.
He's got green eyes.
Kind of what I'm looking for.
[Gabriel] How is everything?
[Kelle] It's amazing.
How are you?
- It's good.
- Good.
- Yeah.
- Good to see you.
[Gabriel]
I'm feeling a little weird.
All these women
are significantly older women,
so it's pretty alarming.
Not in a bad way.
Let's go.
We need to hit the bar.
[Gabriel] But then I started
looking at these women,
and I was like, "Damn,
they are kind of beautiful."
And then my mom's right there
and I was like...
[cell phone vibrating]
Hey, you guys,
I've got this text.
So it says, "Greetings.
You are about to start
a unique dating journey.
All of you have expressed
an openness
to intergenerational dating.
In the real world, there
is often a double standard
where an older man
with a younger woman
is accepted,
but an older woman
with a younger man isn't."
- Mm-hmm.
-"Not here."
Whoo!
[cell phone vibrating]
- [Jose] Okay, I got one, too.
- [Pola] Oh.
"Over the next few weeks,
you'll be part
of a dating experiment
that will level
the playing field
and see if you can find
that special someone
from a different age group."
- [cell phone vibrating]
- I got a text guys.
[all laughing]
"You are not exactly
on the show
you thought you were on.
You are now
in the same dating pool.
Open your minds
and have an experience
you may have never imagined."
Hmm.
I'll be in the hot tub
at 10:00.
[laughter]
Please, Ma,
you gotta chill out.
I'm so excited
to meet these other guys.
Sign me up.
Don't judge me.
Sorry, ladies.
I might be sleeping
with your son.
Looks like we're going
on a date, Harrison.
[Harrison] Yeah, right.
He goes, "Yeah, right."
- Do you need to go home?
- No.
It feels awkward because,
like, I didn't think
it was just gonna be all moms.
[Kelle] I just got here.
[Harrison] I'm not saying
the women are unattractive.
I'm just saying
they all have sons.
And, like,
um, this is gonna be
a weird experience
getting close with the guys,
then, you know, going out
on dates with their mothers.
[Gabriel speaking]
[Pola speaking]
[Soyoung speaking]
She's cutting open people
and stuff.
[Pola] I would die there.
Like, I see
a little bit of blood,
a little bit of blood
and me and you...
you, too, we faint.
Tell them
what your favorite is.
- What do you like to do?
- [Pola] Yeah.
Tell me, tell me.
[Soyoung] Heart surgeon.
- Heart?
- [gasps]
- [Pola] Oh, my God.
You're my hero.
- What?
I am here to find
a special connection,
and I hope my mom also finds
a special connection.
She's getting older, you know,
like she's not really, like,
out there looking
for a lover every day, right?
You're not really,
like, out there
actively searching, are you?
Well, Jimmy thinks so,
but who knows, right?
We might find
the perfect love in here.
Jimmy don't know about me.
It's not the blood
that makes me faint.
It's more so like seeing
the beating heart in a body.
I am open to all ages.
My dating app is set to 65.
I'm close-minded, I guess.
I don't want to date
with 65-years-old man.
[April Jane]
So you're gonna be 24.
- Your son's 23?
- [Kelle] No, he's 20.
[Joey] I'm about 21.
Oh, you're the baby.
And you're gonna be 22, right?
- I'm gonna be 22.
- He said you're both
the same age.
- [laughs]
- Ooh...
[Joey speaking]
And I'm probably the oldest.
Oh, no way.
- There's no way.
- [laughter]
April is the woman
who immediately caught my eye.
I would like to get closer
with April. Who knows?
Maybe I could get her
out of her comfort zone
and show her what it's like
with a younger man.
That's a beautiful ring,
by the way.
[April Jane] Thank you.
[Joey] Kind of reminds me
of your face.
[April Jane laughing]
Younger guys seem like
they have a zest for life.
They're not jaded.
And even though
I'm this age, I...
I've always been very physical
and have a high sex drive.
So if you're gonna have
a younger guy,
there's gonna be
a lot more sex, I would think.
Joey, Joey,
which one's your mom?
- Yeah.
- Ha!
- Just kidding.
- There she is.
You really want me
to point her out?
It's pretty obvious.
Joey is just a young buck,
and he's just probably gonna
do something to my mom and try
and hit on another girl,
then another girl.
So he's not going
anywhere near my mother.
Joey is gonna get a left hook.
- I'm not kidding.
- He's fun.
Joey is...
I'm not worried about Joey.
Gabriel and I are both here
because we wanted
to take this adventure.
It literally fell in our lap
from the heavens, and...
I can't. I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
Just, can you stop
and just let me talk?
Can you do it again?
Can you not say...
why are you saying heavens?
Because
that's what I'm saying.
I am my own person.
But can you stop
interrupting me?
So...
I'm sorry.
[Ryan] Ma, Jose is your man.
Jose looks mad responsible.
- Like, I would trust--
- [Jose] What?
[Ryan] Said you look mad
responsible, like...
like you look
very trustworthy.
Jose, cut the umbilical cord.
No, I mean, we're having
a good conversation.
We're learning a lot here.
- [Pola] We can, we can...
- [Kelle] Pola...
[Jose] You're more than
welcome to join.
There's this super-hot guy
named Jose,
and he seems like a safe bet
because he's
very family-oriented.
You can see, he's like tied
to his mom's hip.
So I feel like he would
definitely just have my back
and be by my side
and, you know,
be in my corner.
[Joey]
I'm not calling you Dad.
[all laughing]
[Kelle] I feel like I need
to get him away from his mom
and then see, you know,
what we can end up doing.
[Gabriel] You're not,
you're not calling him Dad.
You're calling him Daddy.
[all laughing]
No, I'm calling him Daddy.
Oh!
[Kelle laughs]
[Charlene] Out of all
of the women here,
Kelle is definitely going
for all of the attention.
It's almost like
she's campaigning.
You call him father.
It seems like
a lot of work to me.
[Pola] "Attention, daters.
There are eight duos here
and there are eight bedrooms
in the villa.
Each duo will share
a room together."
I'll be honest, I had
concerns about rooming
with Ryan because in the past
I have seen his home.
Mmm, not the child
that I raised,
as far as cleanliness.
We don't get to spend
as much time together
as we used to.
So instead of shading me,
if anything,
this is a moment
to bring us closer together.
"Not all the rooms
are the same.
There are two large
master suites
with hot tubs inside
the room."
- That's crazy.
- Oh, my God.
[Pola] "Head outside,
where the moms
who are the most
in touch with their sons
will win the suites."
[Joey] Okay. Super weird.
When we get the text
that we're gonna be
staying in the same bedroom,
my mom and I were
really close,
but dating lives
are very separate.
I don't want to see
who she's trying to flirt on,
and now we're gonna be
living together.
What did I get myself into?
Who wants to sleep
with their moms?
Weird.
[April Jane] All the young men
take their shirts off.
[Shannan] Who's ready
for a checkup
at the doctor's office?
Oh, that's nice. Oh.
I have no interest in watching
my mom feeling a man.
I'm not here for that.
[Shannan] Nothing wrong
with a little touch and feel.
[Kelle speaking]
[Ryan speaking]
[Ryan] Where are
we going with this?
Are we... you're trying
to get day one strokes?
Like, I don't know.
[Joey] You're joking!
I'm cock-blocking my mom
because you've known him
for six hours.
[Kelle] Calm down. [laughs]
No.
- [April Jane] I have twins.
- [Shannan] Do you?
[April Jane] Three boys.
Gabriel is a twin.
[Shannan] Oh, wow.
[April Jane] But they don't
look alike, fraternal.
- [Shannan] Fraternal.
- [Kelle] So you brought
the ugly one. Thanks.
[laughter]
We get a text.
We have our first challenge,
and all the young men
take their shirts off.
I want you and you
and you and you.
Everyone but me.
Sorry.
The moms get a blindfold
and they have to go up
and touch
all of the young men
and figure out by touching
their chests and abs
and shoulders
which one is their son.
The two moms
that figure out
who their son is
the quickest win
the best suites
in the whole house.
So the competition is on.
I need you guys to help me
find my son
if you want to hang out
with me tonight.
Oh, my God.
[Jose] This challenge is
very important for you to win.
Okay, so be focused,
and we're gonna win.
I want to stay in the suite,
so we have to be careful.
Quick.
Who wants to win?
You've never rubbed me up
and down.
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah.
You don't know
who's who, so...
[Joey speaking]
I'm ready.
I just hope she doesn't go
below the waist
whenever she's
groping these guys,
because that,
that will be out of line.
Out of line.
There's still mommies
in the house!
If I pick Joey, hopefully
I don't pick him first,
because, yeah, we'll have
a nice room, but it's like...
I kind of want more than that.
Hmm.
[April] Not rigid, ain't it?
[Kelle] No.
Ooh.
Mmm...
I don't think so. Nope.
No. Ow.
[laughter]
[Joey] I've never experienced
something like this.
My mom never really shows me
like the younger guys
that she dates.
Or especially, like,
touching them
in front of my face.
I mean, that's...
that's pretty weird to me.
[Kelle] Joey?
This is my son.
Ugh, Ma!
You're one off.
[cheering]
I got Jimmy?
[Joey] Oh, Mom. Ugh!
He got you!
I knew he would.
- [Kelle] Yes! Yes!
- [Joey] I knew he would!
[Kelle] I wanted
you to be my son.
Yeah! Whoo!
Whoo! Yes!
- [Joey] Oh, my God.
- [Soyoung] Kelle gets Jimmy.
And she was
really touchy, touchy.
Fantasy suite! Sorry,
Soyoung.
[Soyoung speaking]
That would have been game, right?
All men touching women.
That would have been killer.
You should've done that.
Here we go.
Who's ready for a checkup
at the doctor's office?
[laughter]
Oh, that's nice.
Oh.
I have no interest in watching
my mom feel on men.
I'm not here for that.
[Shannan] Oh, nice pecks.
Nice traps.
Oh. Mmm.
We are both grown.
And nothing wrong
with a little touch and feel.
- [Ryan] Fine.
- I'm just saying.
Okay.
This feels like my child.
Okay, I'm gonna say yes.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
[Pola speaking
in foreign language]
[Pola] Like I will notice
Jose's shoulder.
It's like very... deep.
I know your shoulders.
Me and Jose train
every day at my studio,
so this is really easy for me.
This is Jose. Oh!
[laughter]
[April Jane] I'm a trainer.
You know,
I appreciate muscle.
So I actually like
this challenge.
I didn't like this challenge.
- That's my Gabriel.
- Yeah.
[Charlene] Harrison.
No?
I was right here.
Well, is there
somebody over here?
Billy.
- Wow.
- That was pretty quick.
This is Billy.
[cheering]
I'm very excited,
so I could feel
the abs a little bit.
Hmm.
[laughter]
Soyoung's style of trying
to pick her son
was very aggressive,
in my opinion.
What?
She's wild.
That's my son.
Yes, it is!
[all laughing]
[producer speaking]
Yeah, he does.
[Gabriel] Can you not...
It sounds so bad. Yeah.
I picked up women, really?
Okay, okay, okay. Okay. Okay.
I won't say that.
I have definitely raised
a gentleman.
Aww.
Guys, I have a text.
"Congratulations.
Your time is a winner."
[cheering and applause]
[Stefany] "You get the suite."
Wow.
Who's the second winner?
Wait, another text message.
I got a text message.
So it says, congratulations.
I was second place.
I get the suite
with a hot tub on the patio.
You're all welcome.
[cheering and applause]
Yeah, Jose!
Jose, I got last.
So you can meet me
at the bungalow outside.
Oh.
[Pola]
I don't get Kelle very well.
She needs to do something
to bring the attention to her.
And I don't think that's nice,
because you don't need
to always be
the center of everything.
I can't.
Sorry,
I can't hear you over there.
[Stefany] Moving in.
[Billy] Are you joking?
[Stefany] Hi,
- welcome to my house.
- Oh, my God.
This is amazing, you know.
- We won.
- Yeah.
- We've won the suite.
- Thank God.
You guys got, like,
a living room area.
- [Stefany] We have everything.
- [Charlene] Wow.
[Billy] I'm stoked about
being able to, like,
get in the sauna.
[Stefany] And then we have
the hot tub, too.
[Billy]
Yeah, that was a plus.
[Stefany] Just don't bring
any of the moms in here.
- Please do not do that.
- Okay, I won't.
[Pola] Wow.
I feel like a queen.
Like the suite is gorgeous.
The space is huge.
- Wow.
- Yeah, that's super cool.
You're not worried
a little bit,
like just sleeping
in a stranger house with--
No, I'm just gonna
stay close to you.
Oh, you have
a good relationship.
- So there's...
- So it's okay, right?
I mean, I guess.
[laughs]
- [Pola]
Everything is beautiful.
- [Jose] Yeah.
[sighs]
You know, it's more common
for the guys to like
the older girls,
you know,
that's kind of a thing.
Like, they have MILF,
they have cougar.
We don't have a cute label
for young guys.
You should just call them
Ryan Jevons.
I'm gonna put that name
on the outside of my room.
I'll see. All right.
See, that's...
I don't know, that could be
taken a lot of ways.
[Ryan] Kelle is not
the natural esthetic
for people that I date,
but Kelle's energy
is tight hot.
Like, her spice level
is at an all-time high.
You never know
what's bound to happen.
What do you think
is the difference between
MILF and cougar?
I'll...
I'll tell you exactly
the difference
because I am still a MILF.
I am not a cougar until
I reach a certain age.
MILF is like
that age between.
[Kelle] I don't look at age, though.
I think that's where society
is totally messed up
because I attract
a lot of younger men
because I have a younger...
- Spirit.
- [Kelle]
...spirit and personality.
I felt a little displaced
just being here
and seeing everyone, you know.
- But it's like...
- Well...
I think, everybody just has
to get out of their shell.
People become too guarded,
then you don't learn anything
and you'll never know
what you'll find.
[Charlene] Yeah,
that's the truth.
- I mean...
- [Ryan] Toast to that.
[Charlene]
I'm actually realizing, like,
this is a chance for us
to learn about ourselves.
Whether we all find
true love or not,
it's an opportunity
for growth,
and there's some
great people here.
Like, let's just enjoy
this moment,
because that's meant to be.
I'm gonna go to the restroom,
so I'm gonna say good night
if I don't see you.
- Good night.
- [Joey] Good night.
I mean,
I honestly learned a lot from,
like all of that talking.
- I mean...
- You did?
Everything that's come out
of his mouth has been
just straight facts.
I'm just wrong.
- You know, I'm just like...
- You're welcome.
This is your dad.
Mom, you gotta be joking.
You know what room we're in.
Although I know
she's got it in her to flirt,
and she does do that a lot,
I've never seen it
firsthand experience.
Ready?
You two,
I'll see you tomorrow.
No, we're going in together.
[Ryan] Sleep easy.
- Still give me love.
- We're going in together.
Bye, Joey.
The reason why we're here
is to date everyone
in the villa,
and I'm taking
that opportunity
so I can make a good decision
on if there would be
a romantic connection
with somebody.
How are we gonna move
your mama out of the room?
[Ryan] Now,
how could I do that?
Can you pick her up?
[Joey] Y'all moving
your mama out of the room?
No!
[Kelle] I'll be kicking
Joey out of my room.
- [Joey] No!
- [Kelle] Bye, Joey.
[Joey] I'm not sleeping
on the bathroom.
Please, no.
For some reason,
I'm immediately drawn to Ryan.
And I mean,
I get it, it's night one,
but I'm very, very open
with sex.
I mean, I would love
to find love if it's here,
but more so, I'm gonna have
a lot of fun.
I'm texting him right now.
[Joey] Mom.
I go, "WYD?"
What are you doing?
Oh, he's messaging me back.
Oh, wait,
I just got a message.
"Where are you?"
You said, "Come up here."
Mom! Mom!
[Kelle speaking]
I'm going to the bathroom.
[Kelle] You go to bathroom.
[Kelle speaking]
If Joey continues
to cock-block me
this entire time,
he's going to ruin
the experience for me.
- [Kelle speaking]
- [Ryan speaking]
The second room on the left.
Oh, my God!
You've got to be joking.
[Ryan] Just chilling.
Bye, Joey.
Don't be a hater, Joey.
Ma, you gotta chill out.
[Kelle] Come upstairs.
So far, we've had
some great conversations.
I've been very open.
I've been very real with her.
So at this point, you know,
where are we going with this?
Are we... you're trying to get
the day one strokes?
Like, I don't know.
[Joey] You're joking!
[Jimmy] We got, like,
moms here.
Like, we got to really
step our game up.
[Gabriel] I'm not like
head over heels for anyone.
Are you?
I mean, I got my eye on one, though.
- That's about it.
- [Gabriel] Who?
- [Jimmy] Pola.
- Pola has these feet that
I just want to, like,
shove them in my mouth.
[laughs]
[Joey] You're joking!
Really not trying
to sleep in here
with Ryan on the other bed.
I'm just telling you
to make sure
you're up in time to go
to the gym in the morning, bro.
- [Kelle] No, Joey.
- [Joey] I'll see you
at the gym tomorrow morning.
All right, tomorrow morning, bro.
- [Kelle] Joey, lay down.
- Make sure you're up.
I'm cock-blocking my mom
because first night, no.
You've known him
for six hours.
You can't just immediately
go into,
you know, I want to...
and then... yeah.
[Kelle] Joey, calm down.
- Calm down.
- No.
I'm not, like,
head over heels for anyone.
Are you?
I mean, I got
my eye on one, though.
- That's about it.
- Who?
- [Jimmy] Pola.
- [Gabriel speaking]
[Jimmy] Yeah.
I find Pola
absolutely beautiful.
I'm a man of great taste.
I like great things.
I'm a very big feet person.
And Pola has these feet
that I just want to, like,
oil up and lather
and just massage
and get real warm
and then paint her toenails
maybe a color and, like,
suck the acrylic off them toes
and shove them in my mouth.
Yeah.
Ha-ha!
We can't be vanilla, bro.
We got, like, moms here.
Like, we gotta really
step our game up.
No.
Wow.
[Jimmy] You think
this is gonna be good?
- [Jose] Dude, it's...
- [Kelle] Wow.
It's a pineapple martini.
[Pola] It looks beautiful.
Thank you.
[Jimmy] So...
- Thank you so much.
- For you, Madame.
- Gracias, senor.
- Oh, you're so welcome.
So, Pola, I was thinking
I really would love
to get to know you
and go on
a paddleboarding date,
maybe if you're,
like, interested.
Yes. That's cool.
Let's do it. Yeah.
So it's down on the beach.
The paddleboards
are over there if you'd like
to go with me.
- [Pola] Yeah.
Let's go. Let's go.
- Let's go.
My mom is picked to go out
on her first date.
I don't know what to think.
Okay.
It's our paddleboards.
[Jose]
It's just that feeling inside
that I don't really
trust these guys yet.
[producer speaking]
[Pola laughing]
Well, yeah. Most of the guys
are too young for my mom.
So have you ever
paddleboarded before?
Actually, I have
a paddleboard just...
- No way, at home in Miami?
- Yeah. I do.
- Oh, it's...
- I do, I do.
Just don't be as naive
as you usually are.
[Pola] I'm sure
he's a nice guy.
Many times the nicest guys
are not the nicest guys.
Just be careful.
Let's go, faster.
[Pola laughing]
[Pola]
I dance classical ballet
since I was four years old.
I love everything that
has to do with physical,
active life.
So if a man cannot keep up
with me physically,
I think I'm not gonna be
attracted to him at all.
And Jimmy, the activity
that he chose, what...
it's exactly
what I really enjoy.
So that's something
that I really like about him.
[Jimmy groans]
Whoo!
At first, I'm really
nervous about Pola and I.
But wow,
she was a very playful person
and I love it about her.
[Pola] All right,
let's go. Let's go.
[Jimmy] She has the idea,
let's do yoga and wants
to do the airplane.
And I'm... I'm so for it.
[Pola chuckles]
I was comfortable being,
you know, on top of her.
Are you ready?
[Pola laughing]
That wasn't good.
It's really fun doing
the airplane
on the board with Jimmy.
And I used to do that
with Jose when he was smaller.
I love to do that with kids.
So this is really fun for me.
Ah, we did it.
[Jimmy] Oh!
I'm super glad that
Jimmy and Pola
are on their mini date
because now I get
a chance to talk to Jose.
He's like super-hot
and I'm hoping to get
to know him better.
I guess we're going
in the bedroom now
that your mom's gone.
[Jose] I guess so.
Kelle is very assertive,
very... very direct in
what she wants.
And I find that
attractive and sexy.
[Kelle] I've never gone paddleboarding.
[Jose] It's super fun.
I'll show you.
It's really cool.
I'll probably have to be
on my knees.
[Jose] Well, you can start
on your knees.
I don't think that
my mom would approve,
but I'm a grown man.
I don't need her approval.
But don't tell her
I said that.
I'm gonna tell Jimmy
to take your mom
all the way over to
that island over there.
[laughter]
We'll stay there
for a couple of days.
Pola, bye.
Pola, I get
the fantasy suite tonight.
[Pola] Never.
Kelle is not the type of girl
for Jose.
I'm 100% sure.
Do you see his body language?
- Look at it.
- [Pola] No.
Whether she likes it or not,
I'm gonna do whatever it takes
to take my man home.
I like to win.
Hey, Mom.
No, I can't.
- Can I steal you?
- Yeah, sure.
- Yeah.
I have a question for you.
- Sure.
I've had my eye on Jose
from day one,
and I'm definitely
going for it.
So, have you ever
dated older women?
I don't think
I asked you that.
Yeah, I usually go for older.
See, and I usually
attract younger men.
Her weak spot in my eyes
are accents, I think.
I think accents
really get her.
It doesn't matter
what you look like.
I think if you have an accent,
you have a chance
with my mom.
You do.
[Kelle] It's really
not about the accent.
It's like they're raised
in a different country,
so they have
a different demeanor
and they treat women differently.
Mm-hmm.
They just so happen
to have an accent.
I don't know why you're, like,
latched on this accent thing.
It's not about the accent.
That's just a bonus,
like, if you ask me.
Are you here...
what are you here for?
- I guess I'm just curious.
- Okay.
I'm here for the same reason
as everybody else is,
I guess, to, um, go outside
of the culture values
that we have and explore
different opportunities,
different relationships,
different connections
with people
that we would never do before.
Am I putting you on the spot?
No. Not at all.
- I mean, on the contrary...
- Sorry.
...on the contrary, actually...
it's actually very,
very cool that...
- I'm just curious.
- Yeah, yeah.
And I appreciate
your question.
Jose and I were
really connecting,
as far as I'm concerned.
I think he moves very slowly,
which I don't like to do,
but I feel like
there's a potential there.
I would love to keep on going
with that conversation.
- [Kelle] Okay.
- For sure.
I was feeling it, too.
[Charlene] Who do I think
will hook up first?
I would probably say Kelle.
Last night
she was all over Ryan.
Now she's after Jose.
But I expect that of her.
She definitely wants to be
the belle of the ball
or the Barbie.
But I think
that it's a little much,
like this isn't a game show.
- [Pola] Salud.
- [Jimmy] Salud.
Oh. So I have to ask.
- What?
- What is your type?
I really like men that like
to do things like
- what we just did.
- Uh-huh.
I don't like men
that just sit down on TV
and just watch TV
and do nothing.
- Yeah.
- [Pola] Yeah. What about you?
Oh, my type. Let's see.
What... what is my type?
- I like dark hair.
- [Pola] You do?
[Jimmy] Good teeth,
good smile.
Being with Pola,
I feel super comfortable.
I'm not even thinking of age.
It just feels very good
and fluid,
and there's no worries
in the world
and we can just be ourselves.
I prefer darker complexion
with green eyes.
[Pola] You do?
- Green... green...
- Me too.
Yeah.
Green is my favorite color.
- Yeah, me too.
- Oh, yeah.
- And dark hair.
- Mm-hmm.
I don't like blonds.
If I would've got green eyes,
it would've been over.
[Pola]
That would've been perfect.
That would've been over
for the world.
I totally feel
a great connection with Jimmy
and I feel really good about
myself with him.
Who do you think Jose likes?
Anybody...
interested in anybody?
- Not really?
- Not yet.
- Not yet?
- No.
It takes him a little time
to build up a little?
No, I would see it.
I don't see his eyes like
shining for anyone.
- Mm-hmm.
- No.
Do you see my eyes shining
for anybody?
- Mmm, yeah.
- Okay. All right.
[laughs]
Oh, la-la.
- We was paddleboarding.
- [Jose] I did see it.
[Kelle] It doesn't look like
paddleboarding to me.
[Pola] We did.
[Jimmy] It's not
what it looks like, I swear.
[Pola] It was really fun.
You want rose, Jose?
[Jimmy] We'll bring you
some rose, Jose.
- No, no, no.
- Beautiful, thank you.
No, drink up.
We have our own rose.
Pola, I get
the fantasy suite tonight.
[Pola] You don't.
You actually don't. Never.
I don't really know
Kelle a lot,
but what I see
and what I feel,
she's really wild,
and I really believe
she's gonna bring drama
to my family, to my son,
and to the relationship
I have between
Jose and myself.
So I don't think
she's the good catch for Jose.
No.
What if Jose falls in love
with Kelle?
No, he won't.
[Jimmy] You see
his body language, though.
- Look at it.
- [Pola] No.
[Jimmy] It's talking.
It's talking to me.
[Pola] No.
No, I know it's not.
- I know him.
- Oh, okay.
Look how close
he is to her face.
- That's an intimate...
- [Pola] Not okay, no.
Pola makes it very clear that
she just does not like Kelle.
So if Kelle wants Jose,
I'm thinking that Kelle's
gonna have to either,
one, go through Pola
or two go around her back.
Kelle.
Kelle without the Y.
Kelle with an E.
I think Jose is open to love
and I'm gonna show him
that I'm the one
he should be with.
- You're mine.
- You like tall men?
- I like confident men.
- Okay.
There's something going on
between me and her.
That could be the start
of something very powerful.
Jose likes very, like,
quiet girls, nice girls.
Mmm.
Kelle is not the type
of girl for Jose.
I'm 100% sure.
So she's not gonna get
anywhere with Jose. Never.
- That's not Jose's style.
- I'm saying--
- That won't happen.
- Hey, Mom.
I'm not sure
if Pola is embracing
this whole situation.
Like, I thought she came
here to date a younger guy,
not her son.
But whether
she likes it or not,
I'm gonna do whatever
it takes to take my man home.
So there is no competition, babe.
If I had a date,
would you want to go with me?
Sure.
I like to win.
- [Pola] It won't happen.
- [Jimmy] But what if?
No, I can't.