[April J] I thought
I had my whole life planned.
But now I'm here.
[cheering]
[April J] I'm just open
to the adventure.
I'm open
to having a connection
with a younger man.
[Ryan] I love older women
that can keep up with me.
I'm looking for love.
I need a grown woman out here.
[Kelle] I have
a very young, free spirit.
And I connect
to younger men,
especially in the bedroom.
[man] You are not
exactly on the show
you thought you were on.
Hey!
[woman] You're about
to embark on a dating
experience like none other.
Err.
[woman] Here we go.
Here we go.
- What's going on?
- [Joey] Wait.
They're our moms.
Holy [bleep].
[April J] I'm gonna have
to see my son date
these moms.
[Harrison] I don't want
to see who my mom's
trying to flirt on.
What did I get myself into?
I'm not mad about my body.
Sorry, ladies.
I might be sleeping
with your son.
[Charlene] Kelle invested
a lot of time into her body,
her sex appeal.
And I know that
young men want that.
It's a little much like
this isn't a game show.
Pola.
I get the fantasy
suite tonight.
[Pola speaking]
[Pola] Kelle is not
the type of girl for Jose.
I'm 100% sure,
she's not gonna get
anywhere with Jose.
Never.
[Jimmy] You see his body
language, too. Look at it.
[Kelle] Whether
she likes it or not.
I'm gonna do
whatever it takes
to take my man home.
[Jimmy] We got
to watch out for her.
- [Pola] It won't happen.
- But what if.
No, I can't.
I like to win.
[Pola] Oh, my God.
[Kelle] The sun is shining,
an amazing day.
[Joey] And I just love
looking at the lady's bodies
and I'm just getting
to know them.
It's a good start
to the day.
My mom does get
a lot of attention
from here up,
mainly because
she never wears bras
and the girls are always
popping out.
You know, the headlights
are always on, so.
[Kelle] It didn't bother you
when you were a baby
sucking on 'em either.
- So, let's keep it real.
- [Joey laughs]
'Cause I needed
the milk, Mom.
I needed some energy.
You were really thirsty.
[both chuckles]
From the places you've been,
which is your favorite place?
So far, I love Costa Rica.
- Yeah?
- [Kelle] I've only gone once.
And when I went,
I went with somebody
that I didn't really know,
but I'm like a risk taker.
- I'll just do it, you know.
- Okay.
[Kelle] I feel like
Jose is interested in me.
Maybe I'm gonna
take a little bit more.
- Baby, take whatever you want.
- No.
Okay, fine.
But I feel like I need
to get him away from his mom.
She's great,
but she seems to be, like,
showing up every time
I like, try and talk to him.
I want to get a cup
for us for the drinks.
Do you want another one?
- I'll get one.
- All right.
[Kelle speaking]
- [Jose speaking]
- I need my drink.
[Jose] Yes.
- So, Pola.
- Yes.
I'm taking your son
out on a date.
- You are?
- Yeah, why not?
I haven't told him yet.
No?
I don't like to say
what I'm gonna say,
but I really feel that
Kelle is, like, easy,
and I don't like that.
I know for Jose
it's really important
to have values.
So, I really don't believe
Kelle is the right girl
for Jose.
When?
[Kelle] I'm not telling you,
you'll interfere.
I told your mom
I'm gonna take you out
on a date.
[Jose] Okay.
Let's go.
[Kelle] She wanted to know
when, I said she can't know
'cause she'll interfere.
[Jose]
She doesn't need to know.
Because right now
we're all in the same villa.
It's gonna be a little bit
difficult to separate
my mom and myself
in regards of dating
other women.
And so, I think
we have to get
a little bit creative.
We're kicking
you out of your room, too.
[laughs]
[Pola] I don't see
Jose in a situation
where he's dating a girl
like Kelle.
He always dates
very quiet girls.
And I think
she's really wild.
So, I don't see
Jose going far with her.
Never.
[Kelle] Maybe we can rock,
paper, scissors over it.
- Thanks.
- [Jose] Yeah.
I think
Ryan is the most,
like, sexual like,
would be like,
know what to do.
[Soyoung speaking]
Exactly.
I mean, I don't mind
chasing, but I don't...
I feel like I have to,
like, test it damn myself.
No, you can't.
Really...
Why should we have to do that?
[Soyoung speaking]
...because I have this list.
Nobody fits in my list,
so nobody can keep up
with me, really.
You're still sitting there
waiting like nothing's
ever come, so.
You don't know
what you want, yeah?
I do know...
You might be closing
yourself off and nothing
can meet those standards.
Well, that's why you have
to have a little standard
to get the right one.
- Yeah.
- If you don't have
that standard,
how are you gonna
have what you want?
I feel like my first initial
thing was like Jose's.
- Probably the most.
- Yeah. Yes, yes.
[Soyoung speaking]
[Charlene] I think
Jose is hot.
I already know
all of the moms here
love Jose.
He's very intriguing.
He definitely gives me
the impression that
he knows
what to do with a woman
in the bedroom.
He knows how to take control.
He has that get
the job done mentality.
Mm-hmm.
That's how I feel.
Oh, my God.
We had the same.
Yeah.
[laughs]
- That's a good spot.
- Mm-hmm.
That's always a good
spot for every...
[cell phone buzzing]
Oh, wait, guys.
- I got a text.
- [man] You got to take it.
[April W] I know.
It's time to play
Wall of Secrets.
If you can stump
your mom or son
with a secret
that they don't know,
you win a romantic date.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Yeah. Yeah. Let's go.
[April J] Each week
we have a challenge
and this week
it's called Wall of Secrets.
We're supposed to guess
our son's secret.
The son is supposed
to guess our secret.
And if neither of us
guess each other's secret,
we win a date
with whoever we'd like.
[April J speaking]
[woman speaking]
[Joey] So last night
we got a text that
we need to write down
some of our deepest,
darkest secrets that
no one knows about.
What we didn't know
is that we're gonna be
revealing these
to the entire house.
Ooh.
This is crazy.
And not only that,
but the secret that
we're sharing,
we got to guess
if it's yours, if it's mine.
- [Kelle speaking]
- [man speaking]
[Kelle speaking]
The whole point
is to stump each other.
I think I got this.
Or I'm gonna just go up
and I'm gonna say
whichever is the craziest
one I'm picking.
I don't know,
you got April over there.
Okay, here we go.
- Wish me luck.
- Bye.
[Kelle] Bye.
She's so cute.
Oh, here I am
at the Wall of Secrets.
Okay.
So, I had sex in a mall
elevator after watching
a late night movie.
That actually sounds
like it would be fun.
This one is just horrendous.
I slept
with my son's best friend.
That is just...
That's...
That's unacceptable.
I started dating
a couple of women,
but they were both
just a hit and quit.
I never called them again.
That better not be Gabriel,
because I did not raise
my Gabriel like that.
But I know
which one would be Gabriel.
Possibly Gabriel has had
a seven woman orgy.
Not proud of it,
but that could be
my kid right there.
Okay.
This might be the walk
of shame here.
I'd have to figure out
which one is Ryan's.
He knows who I date
and what my type is.
But you know things
about my sex life.
- No.
- Yeah, I can do
without getting terms.
I don't...
I don't share that with him.
- I can do without
getting terms.
- I don't share that.
And I don't want to know his.
I had a quicky on a yacht
with a girl I just met.
Yeah.
Yeah, that could
potentially be him.
When I was 16,
I had a three-way
with two girls
at my mom's house.
He better not have.
I hope that would not be him.
I started dating
a couple of women
but they were both
just a hit and quit it,
and I never called them again.
He probably had ghosted them.
I grinded on a grandma
and she liked it.
Hmm.
It says really hard. Okay.
I got pink eye
from [bleep] ass.
What?
[Billy] I got pink eye
[bleep] ass.
I don't think my mom
would do that.
I got a pink eye
from [bleep] ass.
You could catch a lot
of freaking pink eyes and...
Hmm.
Salmonella.
Salmonella?
Yew.
Yeah, it's poop, you know.
Oh, that...
that's definitely not my son.
If he got pink eye
from [bleep] ass.
Oh, my God, mom.
Oh.
I can look back
at the doctor records,
just saying.
We got a [bleep] group
of people here.
I dated my son's middle
school teacher.
I mean, I wouldn't know this,
but that could be my mom.
I started dating
a couple of women,
but they were both
just a hit and quit.
I never called them again.
That's Jose.
I've had sex
in public on a beach.
My mom goes to a lot
of nude beaches, so.
I had sex in a restroom
with a stranger.
He was young and very hot.
That's giving Kelle vibes.
I had sex in the mall
elevator after watching
a late night movie.
I think that might be my mom.
She's kind of kinky like that.
I'm interested
in seeing what he picked.
[Jimmy] I kissed
my male friend
for New Year's Eve,
and that's when
he told me he was bisexual.
Definitely could be my mom.
I had a seven woman orgy.
Are you kidding me?
Could that be my mom?
Oh, my. God.
Oh, my God.
What?
[Harrison speaking]
[Charlene] I make
the most out
of my elevator experience,
you know that since
you were kids.
- Oh, I...
- We jump, it's a whole thing.
We jump.
It's too much information.
I slept with my...
Wait, I slept
with my son's best friend.
Wow.
Okay.
I think April W slept
with her son's best friend.
That's either
April W or April J.
Mine's...
mine's bad.
Mine's bad, too.
Which one's my mother?
I got a text, everyone.
Yay!
[April J] Now that
you've all had a chance
to guess,
it's time to reveal
who was able to stump
their mom
or son with their deep,
dark secret.
Everyone needs to fess up.
Oh, my God.
Seriously?
[indistinct chatter]
[Ryan] I think potentially
these secrets could cause
drama because
I think a lot of people
will use these secrets
as a moment
to judge character.
Oh, my gosh.
I had a seven woman orgy.
[cheering]
[Pola speaking]
Well, I don't know
what they're talking about.
You don't really like
the Spanish talk?
No, I think it's rude.
Honestly,
it's getting annoying.
Are you guys done
speaking Spanish?
She becomes like fire.
You go speaking
when you're by yourself.
It's fine.
Like...
Oh, no.
I'm the bad one.
[April J] It's time to reveal
who is able to stump
their mom or son
with their deep, dark secret.
Oh, my God.
Seriously?
[laughs]
[woman] No, I don't know.
[April J] I thought
I wouldn't have to say
which one was mine.
And I feel very nervous
revealing my secret.
I'm gonna start with my son,
Gabriel over here,
and I hope it's not true, but...
I had a seven woman orgy.
Yes.
- [Soyoung] Yes?
- No?
- [Gabriel] No.
They're always all over you.
Like I would tell you guys.
[Soyoung] No.
Loser.
[woman] No.
I guessed that my mom
[bleep] my middle school teacher.
[gasping]
[Ryan] Why are you laughing?
Was I right?
I hope it's not true.
No, you're wrong.
Who would you think
that I would...
[Gabriel] Oh.
[indistinct chatter]
That wasn't hers.
I win.
[woman] Yeah.
[Gabriel] Oh.
We won.
So, we stumped each other.
- But...
-'Cause we always win.
But does that mean
you're gonna hear
what my secret is?
Oh, no.
I better.
I think this is...
Now we got to tell
each other our secrets.
No, I don't want
to tell you my secret.
Please tell me
your secret's not
the one of sleeping
with your son's best friend.
All right, April.
Okay.
Gabriel, do you want to...
cover your ears maybe?
So, I was making a lot,
and I went with my boyfriend
to our friend's house,
and I...
I woke up
with his best friend.
That's not that bad.
[indistinct chatter]
Mine was kind of lame.
I was on New Year's once,
and I was surrounded by,
like, my best friend
and all his, like, sisters.
And it's just like
[bleep] And I was like...
I was like [bleep]
Like I've never kissed
a guy before.
So, like,
we kissed for a second.
I stopped,
and then he was like,
why did you stop?
And he loved it.
And then ever since then,
I think that's how he kind
of realized maybe he like...
likes everyone.
So that was the bisexual.
Oh.
[Ryan] I'll be honest,
though, you got to take
your hat off to that.
If you can be enlightening
enough to tell somebody
you made them
realize their sexuality
and like pretty much
give credit to yourself
in that,
like that's a hell
of a egotistical transition.
Like, that's...
that's crazy.
I... I would say
he has a pretty healthy ego.
Yeah.
Help me, Jesus.
Come on, Stephany.
So, the one
I picked for Billy was...
I've had sex in public
on the beach.
Yeah.
[cheering]
[Stefany] He's always
at the beach.
[man] He's always
at the beach?
Always.
[Kelle] Billy's secret was sex
on the beach is kind of
a little enticing
since the beaches, right?
[Joey] Enticing?
Wha...
Enticing.
[Billy] The one
I had for my mom is
I dated my son's
middle school teacher.
- [Stefany] He got it.
- [all] Oh.
[Stefany] He got it.
- [woman] They won.
- [Joey] Nope.
We got it.
[Kelle] They thought
they guessed it right
that they won.
But it...
But it was the opposite.
And they actually lost.
Charlene.
Okay, so it's my turn, guys.
I guessed for Harrison
that he said I grinded
on a grandma and she liked it.
[gasping]
[woman] Oh, my God.
[cheering]
[Harrison] Back
when I was a dancer,
a male entertainer.
Whoa.
[Shannon]
That piqued my interest.
That's all I got to say.
I was like I need a date
with Harrison.
So, we know it's in him.
It's like, who's just
gonna pull it out of him
is the question.
Well, he pulled it out.
[laughs]
The secret that I guessed
for my mom was that
she kissed my male friend
for New Year's Eve
and that's when he told me
he was bisexual.
- [man] Whoa.
- No.
See I said I hooked up
with the 23-year-old,
and I might not have
remembered his name.
[Kelle] Oh.
[Charlene] So did we win?
Like...
[Harrison] No.
You guessed mine right.
Yeah.
I mean, come on.
You were a dancer, right?
Well, actually,
the word is male entertainer.
Well, stripper
or male entertainer.
Okay, next one.
Kelle.
[indistinct chatter]
Oh, Joey.
[Kelle] For Joey, I...
I guessed I had sex
in a mall elevator after
watching a late night movie.
No.
Joey ain't that cool.
Mine was the hit it
and quit it.
I hit it and quit it
within the first couple
of days.
Multiple girls
and I never talked
to them again.
[gasping]
Oh.
[Joey] All right. The one that
I guessed for my mother was...
I have had sex
in public on the beach.
- No.
- Really?
- No, that wasn't...
[Kelle] Mine was I had sex
in a Michelin restaurant
in London with a stranger.
- Oh.
- Oh, my God.
So that's why
you've been going
to Europe for so long?
[woman] I like her.
- So...
- We stumped each other.
- ...I guess...
- So, we won.
I guess we won.
- We won.
- Yeah.
We didn't lose.
We won.
Well, who are you
taking on a date?
I don't know.
[Stefany speaking]
[Pola speaking]
[Billy] I was, like,
actually pretty shocked
when it came
to Kelle's secret.
I thought it would be
a little bit more exciting.
I actually thought that
it would definitely be
the one that she slept
with her son's best friend.
Really?
I thought it might have
been the seven woman orgy.
So, I guessed for Ryan
that he's dated
a couple of women,
that he just hit it
and quit it and never
called them again.
- [Kelle] Yay!
- Nope.
No.
Just...
[Ryan] I was involved
with seven women
in a one-time situation
for a night for my birthday.
I knew he was like
a man whore,
but not on that level.
[cheering]
And everybody was happy.
[Billy] I'm not gonna lie, Ryan.
That's pretty dope.
Pretty sure all the guys
in the room are pretty
jealous of you right now.
Lord, help me.
I need a beverage after that.
Maybe grossed out.
I would never guess
in 10,000 years.
That's a lot of years.
That's before Christ and some,
that you would have been
with seven women at one time.
Never.
Seven days in a week.
Yeah, seven doors.
No, no.
All right.
Where you at?
So pre your dad...
pre your dad,
guy I was dating,
went to the movies
and had a nice time
at the elevator.
[cheering]
[Shannon] And I'm just
thankful that the pressure
of winning a challenge
is now off of me.
I can't unhear your escapades.
At least you didn't see.
Thank God.
Whoosah.
[Soyoung] All right, now I go.
[Jimmy] All right,
all right, all right.
All right.
[Soyoung] Let me
pick up Jimmy's secret.
Okay.
Oh, I got pink eye
from [bleep] ass.
[Kelle] Yeah.
Real, real, real.
[Soyoung] Real.
Do it.
[woman] I do it.
It's a normal thing.
[Ryan] What?
Not the pink eye part.
That just happens 'cause
when you're going up
and down,
up and down,
back and forth.
[laughs]
[Pola] When Jimmy
starts talking to us
about what he did, I...
I was like thinking about
what he was doing
and how he was doing it.
So, it was a little bit
complicated just to take
him out of the picture
and just see Jimmy as Jimmy.
But I'm glad
he didn't kiss me in our date.
After what...
what I heard
about Jimmy doing.
No.
No way.
[laughs]
Oh, my God.
The commotion in this room.
All right, all right.
This is what I guessed
for my mom.
- I guessed...
- I don't know
if you could guess, though.
I kissed my male friend
New Year's Eve,
and that's when he told me
he was bisexual.
Nope.
And...
[Ryan] Well,
we don't even know
our mom's crazy.
You guys don't know your mom.
- We don't know our mom.
- [Jimmy] All right.
Amma.
I don't want to explain.
I'm just gonna answer.
How's that?
Explain.
- [Soyoung] No.
- Explanation.
No, I don't want
to explanation.
Everybody explained.
Well, start
and then we'll see.
[Soyoung] Okay.
My secret is I slept
with your best friend.
Whoa.
[Soyoung] Okay. My secret is
I slept with your best friend.
Whoa.
There's no way.
Did you know that?
No.
Does it look like
I knew that.
This is something
I never saw coming.
I did not expect this at all.
0%.
And I thought
I knew my mom really well.
I don't know
what to think about it.
Look, look,
I don't need an explanation.
I'm a little traumatized
right now.
I'm not gonna lie.
We thought Ryan was a savage.
Yeah.
We're all in shock.
[Kelle] Joey's best friends
kind of have been with him
since elementary school.
That would be a boundary
I would never cross.
[chuckles]
[Jimmy] Why would
you put that down?
I knew
you're not gonna get it.
Okay.
So, say it.
So, I put it down because
I thought,
you're not gonna get it.
You want me to...
[Jimmy speaking]
[laughs]
Soyoung likes them so young.
Are we done?
[Gabriel] That's the most
savage thing I think
anyone did.
[Soyoung] Yes.
- [cell phone buzzing]
- [Ryan] It was so cold, though.
The winners
of our Wall of Secrets
challenge are...
Ryan and Shannon,
Kelle and Joey,
Gabriel and April.
You are the three... Wait.
You are the three
mother son duos
who stumped each other.
And now for your prize,
Ryan, Joey and Gabriel.
You won a group date
next week and will be
able to take whoever you want.
[cheering]
[Ryan speaking]
I'm excited that
we have won something finally.
Something.
Ooh.
By way of us winning
and how we won, I'm horrified.
[Ryan speaking]
- You see?
- We finally win something.
Just finished
the Wall of Secrets.
Damn.
It's not what I thought
it would be like at all.
Honestly, this one hits deep.
This one...
This one I did not see
coming at all.
Honestly.
Hmm.
My mom...
she really dropped
one on me that.
You know, it's just like
I don't even want to know
something like that.
I feel like she should've took
that to her grave
or something.
I don't really know
what to feel.
I don't know how I feel.
I hope nobody
really talks about it.
I don't want to know about
who it was with
or even hear about it
anymore honestly.
Right now [bleep].
[Charlene speaking]
[Jimmy speaking]
[Charlene] I think
Jimmy's having a hard time
because he wasn't ready
for his mom's secret,
and I feel like Harrison
would be acting the same way.
[Charlene speaking]
[Jimmy speaking]
- [Soyoung] Mia.
- [Jimmy] What?
[Soyoung] Let's go to bed.
[Jimmy] Amma.
Life's crazy.
It's crazy.
- [Charlene speaking]
- [Jimmy] No.
[Soyoung speaking]
[Jimmy speaking]
- [Soyoung speaking]
- [Jimmy] Yes.
[Soyoung speaking]
[Jimmy] No.
No.
[Soyoung speaking]
[Jimmy speaking]
[Jimmy] Um, honestly.
I'll listen to you.
[Soyoung speaking]
No, it's not about talk.
Everything's understood.
Everything is.
When I go in the room
we're not gonna talk.
I understand.
[Jimmy] Okay.
And it's okay.
[Soyoung speaking]
Ah, it's not too far.
You haven't seen too far.
You don't live in my world.
- You've never seen too far.
- [Soyoung] Okay. Okay.
[Jimmy] Go home.
[Jimmy speaking]
Right?
Look.
It gets...
it gets difficult in life, right?
It's surreal.
And you know what,
you want to run away.
Hmm.
I didn't expect
this at all, really.
I feel guilty.
But I'm a human.
I'm a woman, too.
I mean, if...
[Soyoung speaking]
[Soyoung] I'm hoping
he will forgive me.
[sobbing]
[Soyoung speaking]
Either Pola is a helicopter
mom or a jealous wife.
He likes what he likes.
[Pola speaking]
- Yes, he does.
- [Pola speaking]
I'm zero jealous.
I'm really not jealous at all.
[cheering]
I have a surprise for you.
It is intriguing.
[Kelle] Even though
we did not win this challenge,
I've gotten to arrange
a date for Jose and I.
I feel like I need
to get him away
from his mom
because she like seems to be,
like showing up every time
I like try and talk to him.
I know you're from Mexico,
so I planned, like,
a little date for us.
Okay.
To show you one
of the landmarks of Mexico.
Okay. Which... which is...
Can't tell you.
You're gonna see when we...
Okay, I'm excited.
Yeah.
And we're going by boat.
Okay.
Amazing.
Thank you, senorita Kelle.
It's fun.
I'm not sure
what kind of surprise
she has for me,
but I really liked that Kelle
took initiative to go
on a date.
I found that quite sexy.
I think that my mom
would have some
reservations about her,
but I'm pretty sure my mom
would appreciate a woman
taking care of her son
and being thoughtful.
I got it.
Look at the service.
- Wow.
- Ah.
Five star service.
Thank you. Hi.
- [man] How are you?
- [Kelle] Good. How are you?
Since Jose is from Mexico.
I want to take him
to one of the biggest
landmarks in Mexico,
which is a mushroom rock.
I've set up this date
because I'm hoping that
my efforts that
I'm putting into this date,
I hope he actually sees that
I'm really interested in him.
So, this is the place
that you brought me?
- Yeah.
- This is the mushroom rock.
- I've seen that online.
I...
I wanted to come here.
- Do you love it?
- Yeah, I love it.
Thank you. And I'm happy
to share this with you.
Like, I'm really,
really happy.
Kelle has a very strong
personality, and that's
something that I admire.
But also,
she has a very caring
loving side.
I like that she's beautiful
and thoughtful.
And I might want to see
more of that softer side.
So, I want to talk
about things that...
that are amazing about you.
- About me?
- Yeah.
That caught my...
my attention a lot.
Like the... the way that
you manage your space,
how you shine
wherever you go,
how you stick to your gut,
to yourself.
So, it's very admirable.
- I'm glad you like it.
- For sure.
I actually...
Um, I don't really know
what to say.
You actually make me
a little bit speechless sometimes.
- [Jose] Why?
- Which is rare...
because I always
have a good comeback...
- [Jose] something to say?
- ...or something silly
or something funny to say.
But, um, I don't know,
I'm just really drawn to you.
So, I feel like
I get a little bit of nervous
or something around you.
Which is weird.
I'm glad that we do have
this time to get to know
each other better because,
you know, I think
very highly of you.
- Thank you. I appreciate it.
- Yeah.
And I adore your mom,
so I would love for her
to be my mother in law when...
I don't get hit on a lot
when I go out
and I feel like a lot
of people tell me that
I'm a very intimidating person
which I feel it's so hard
for me
to believe because I'm...
I don't really feel like
I give off that persona.
But with Jose,
giving me a list
of amazing attributes of me.
I'm not used to somebody
doing that,
especially on a first date.
So, it was really exciting to,
you know, hear
how he felt about me.
Oh-oh.
Knew that was coming.
The way you were
looking at me that whole time.
- Yeah?
- [chuckles]
Now I'm just like, whoo!
I feel like he was feeling
what I was feeling
at the same moment.
He left me wanting more.
That's all I could say.
So far, being alone,
with us in the water
has been amazing.
Being here and seeing
this beautiful sunset and...
and how beautiful you look.
This is a really special
moment as well.
[Soyoung speaking]
[Pola speaking]
No, he's okay.
He's a man now.
Yes.
He's a man.
[Soyoung speaking]
He's a man now.
- [Pola laughs]
- He's a man now.
[Soyoung speaking]
Yeah, but he likes
what he likes.
[Pola speaking]
- Yes, he does.
- [Pola speaking]
[Pola] It's really
important for me to have
a good man by my side.
So, I want the same
for Jose,
I want him to find
a nice girl for him.
Where's everybody?
He been gone for 5 hours.
He obviously like something.
[Pola speaking]
[laughs]
[Kelle] Hola.
[cheering]
[Joey] Oh, you guys look good.
[Pola speaking]
[Joey] Spill the cheese.
Spill the cheese.
[Pola] Hola.
[Jose] Spill the cheese?
Yeah, you guys were
gone for a long time.
[woman] Yes.
Any intimacy?
- And...
- [Ricky] No?
[Ryan] Now throw
her the question.
[man] You don't
kiss and tell,
what you're gonna do.
[Jose] I don't even know
what to say.
My mom is there.
I had... I had a great
time, but I don't know
how to express myself.
Everything is blowing
my mind, honestly.
Okay. Okay. Okay, listen.
Since Jose is from Mexico,
I took him to like,
one of the biggest
landmarks of Mexico.
- [Jose] Yeah.
- And we had the most
amazing time.
[Ricky] What landmark is it?
It's called the mushroom...
the mushroom rock.
Ah, I wanted to go there.
We talked about it.
- [Pola speaking]
- [Jose] Yeah.
[Pola speaking]
Maybe next time
you can take me.
- No.
- Yeah.
[Jose] Well,
we had a great time.
It was really,
really amazing.
Yeah.
[Pola] It's fine.
I'm... I'm fine.
I'm fine with it.
I'm zero jealous.
I'm really not jealous
at all.
It was a boat for two?
Yeah.
It was a boat for us.
So, you guys got
a hotel room or something?
[Jose] A gentleman
never speaks about that
stuff with anybody else.
That's why I love you.
[Kelle] Pretty sure Jose
is not on this retreat
to date his mama.
Wham.
We're jealous.
Either Pola is a helicopter
mom or a jealous wife.
[laughs]
[Stefany speaking]
[Kelle] Okay.
No speaking in Spanish,
we don't know.
The majority doesn't know
what you're saying.
I don't know
what they're talking about,
that they can't speak
in English.
You're exploiting people.
It what's you're doing.
But it has nothing
to do with you.
What is wrong with her?
[Stefany speaking]
[Kelle speaking]
[cheering]
You really can't beat
tacos and tequila.
Is there a shrimp
taco somewhere?
That's a beef.
That's beef.
It ain't nowhere.
[speaking spanish]
[Ryan] We finally get to see
the house let loose.
[Joey] I didn't think
Soyoung would be so, you know,
active about her dance moves.
I mean, she really
started going crazy.
It blew me away.
'Cause she's Soyoung.
Yeah.
[Kelle] I think Mama Pola
forgot to cut
the umbilical cord
when he was born.
I feel like
it's uncomfortable,
Jose to date me,
like with his mom right there.
Clearly, there's some
sort of attachment disorder
going on between
Pola and Jose.
So, I'm like...
Jose.
[Pola speaking]
Okay.
Pola.
Go.
I'm frustrated with myself
for not knowing Spanish
because Jose and Pola
are speaking Spanish
very fluently
'cause it's like their
first language.
[Pola] I don't know
why she's staring at us
so much.
- I don't know.
- Like... did I...
did I any...
Did I do anything wrong?
I mean,
you didn't do anything.
- So, what... What's going on?
- I don't know. I don't know.
[Pola speaking]
They're...
Well, I don't know
what they're talking about.
Maybe they're talking
about us, but it's like
I just...
I just want to be
a part of whatever.
Yeah. You want to...
you want to be in the know.
[Stefany speaking]
She would take my bed,
and then I'll sleep
on the couch.
[Pola speaking]
[Charlene] Pola and Stefany
and Jose are speaking Spanish.
You know,
and their little group
is definitely making
everybody feel uncomfortable.
For me, I want to know
what you're saying.
And if you don't want me
to know, then, like,
go somewhere else.
[Kelle] Okay.
No speaking in Spanish,
we don't know.
The majority doesn't know
what you're saying.
[indistinct chatter]
I spoke Spanish and English.
I don't know.
You don't really like
the Spanish stuff?
No, I think it's rude.
I don't know
what they're saying.
I think it's disrespectful, honestly.
Are we speaking in German?
Oh.
[Stefany speaking]
[Ricky speaking]
[Kelle] Yeah, dude. Enough.
Come on.
We don't know.
We don't know
what you're saying.
- English, Stefany. English.
- [Kelle] Not fair.
The fact that Pola
keeps speaking in Spanish
with Stef and Jose,
I don't know what
they're talking about that
they can't speak
in English about.
So, it's honestly,
it's getting annoying.
[Stefany speaking]
[Pola speaking]
[Kelle] Oh.
Are you guys done
speaking Spanish?
[Stefany speaking]
- [Kelle] It's rude.
- No.
I'm telling you it's rude.
Oh, no, no.
It's just a bad habit.
- Bad habit.
- It's rude.
It's my first language.
Our first language.
But you're not...
you're not here to speak
your first language.
[indistinct chatter]
But it's rude
when you do that
in front of other people
like Ricky or me.
Do you speak Spanish?
- No, but we're...
we're translating with Ricky.
- [Ricky speaking]
[Kelle]
But they're translating.
Yeah, we translate.
We... Well, whatever
they want you to think
that they're saying.
[Pola] No, no, no.
We're not that kind of people.
We won't do that to you,
to you or to anyone.
Listen, if had anything
bad to say to you,
I'll tell it to your face.
I'm not gonna
translate to her.
Come on.
What is wrong with her?
Why can't we speak Spanish?
I'm telling you,
if we have something
to say bad, we'll tell her.
[Pola speaking]
[Stefany] I mean,
maybe she is self-conscious, insecure.
I don't know.
It's not about me thinking
you're talking about me.
Just ask us.
It's about respect.
Next time...
next time...
You know, we'll create
a group setting where
everyone speaks English...
[Stefany] Usually
when I speak that language...
when I talk, I'm next to her,
I'm gonna talk to her Spanish.
[indistinct chatter]
[Jose] I hear a lot
of screaming downstairs
and I hear Kelle is the one
that's screaming.
She's still going around
the same thing about
the language barrier.
This is so dramatic
and unnecessary.
I should stop this.
[Kelle] Oh,
what are you talking about?
- So, it's fine.
- [Stefany] What is the matter?
We speak languages.
Then go speak it
when you're by yourself.
- [Pola] No.
- [Pola speaking]
[Jose speaking]
[Kelle speaking]
[Jose] Seeing that situation,
it actually showed
a little bit on the other side
the darker side of Kelle
that I didn't know.
And I don't find it
attractive.
[Pola speaking]
[sighs]
[Stefany] If I have
something to say,
I don't need to talk
to somebody else in Spanish.
I'll tell her directly.
I actually...
I never even thought of this.
We're in Mexico.
We could speak Spanish.
And if you don't understand,
too bad.
Kelle, where are you?
It's me, Stef.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
I don't want you
to feel like that.
I swear we're not talking
bad about you.
No, you guys are like
laughing at me.
[Stefany] Why would
we laugh about you?
No, because you're like,
oh, we would never,
like talk about you.
It has nothing to do
with you.
I could speak Spanish
all day with her,
here, down there.
But I think
there's other people
that maybe if they just...
Okay. Well, then
have them come to me.
Because her
and I are talking...
- But you guys don't care.
- ...about family and kid...
You guys don't care.
[Pola speaking]
- Right. But that's not...
- She's still...
Yeah.
But don't...
don't capture that energy.
She becomes like fire.
Like it's...
I don't like people
being disrespectful.
- I'm not like that.
- I know.
- So, I don't feel comfortable.
- I agree, I...
She's shouting at me,
just like...
I'm not used
to people like that.
Right.
Like, I feel
I'm really well educated.
I mean, we can talk,
we can speak.
- It's fine.
- [Jose] Yeah.
Like, the action of it
is just shouting without
a reason or anything.
- You're exploiting people.
It's what you're doing.
- [Stefany] No.
- No, no, no. No, no, no, no.
- Oh, you all are.
- It's what you're doing.
- [Stefany] No.
[Jose] It's starts to give me
some second thoughts
about her.
Hopefully you're gonna
meet another woman
from there
and leave Kelle just
by its side.
By side.
[Jose speaking]
Hopefully.
Cool.
Now I'm the bad guy.
I'm not the bad guy,
'cause I don't speak Spanish.
[Stefany speaking]
[laughs]
[bleep]
We want you to come up
with a dance that best
communicates design.
[cheering]
[Jose] The shirt comes off
and all the ladies go crazy.
[cheering]
[Gabriel] So, I'm excited
for my first date,
I get to go out the villa.
I've never been
on a double date
with my mom before.
I would have never thought
that I would be here
with such a beautiful woman.
[April J] I honestly
can't remember the last time
I had so much fun on a date.
[Gabriel] He's trying to hit
on my mom
and it's not sitting
right with me.
To me, personally, you're
the most intriguing person
in the house.
I want to be with Jose.
- I love my son.
- Okay.
It is a bit of mama's boy
going on with Jose and Pola.
They don't really have
the right sized condoms
for me here.
He said he has a big [bleep].
How does it make you feel?
[laughs]
[Ryan speaking]
He's already
asking my girl on a date.
Who?
You and I?
I do Gabriel a lot,
but I'm a little confused
at this point.
[Ryan speaking]
It's about to get
a little more dramatic.