[woman] Previously
on MILF Manor...
[Billy] Kelle doesn't really
mind PDA.
But with my mom being around,
it's a little weird.
I definitely am not enjoying
this one bit.
She could tone it down
a little bit.
Oh, my goodness.
I can't watch.
[Kelle] I said,
take it off, Billy.
[Billy chuckles]
[Billy] I don't think
I can stay here.
I don't really like
the comfort of this bed.
[Kelle] I just don't have time
to play games.
But if you wanna go
sleep with your mom...
enjoy.
[Kelle]
Every time I'm close to you...
- [Ryan] Okay.
- You're looking at me.
Lot of passion.
I really feel a connection
with him.
This is the guy.
- Salud to life.
If you could put
sunscreen on me.
[Joey] The lower arms...
A little massage
along with it.
Oh, I love it.
[April] Out of all
the young men in the house,
I'm sort of gravitating
to the youngest guy.
You're really special.
- You're special!
- Thank you.
Jose gives me a lot of
butterflies and nervous
and I get giggle
and I don't know what to do.
[kisses]
How do you feel when you
see the exterior of me?
I mean, I see your elegance.
- That's hot.
- [Shannan] I like Jose.
He's my one and only.
He has my attention.
But we would
have to sneak out.
I know that Jose
has been dating
a lot of women in the house,
but tonight,
I'm gonna show him that
I'm the one he should be with.
[Shannan] Did you guys
see this?
[Kelle] I'm sure
the other women here
are gonna lose their
[bleep] man.
[chuckles softly]
[Pola] So, Jose
is not in my room.
I have no idea why.
He never does that.
If he was thinking
of not coming home,
he would've told me.
I have no idea
what's going on.
Like, I tried to text him,
but I haven't had any answer
and that's really weird.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
[Jose] My relationship
with Kelle has been
full of ups and downs.
We started very well
at the Mushroom rock.
- Do you love it?
- Yeah, I love it.[chuckles]
Thank you and I'm happy
to share this with you.
Uh-oh.
And then with some
of the disagreements
and the shouting...
it went a little bit down.
You're not here to speak
your first language.
[indistinct conversation]
- We're talking together--
- But it's rude!
She's shouting at me,
just like...
You think they noticed
that we've gone?
Let's not think
about them, please.
- [Kelle] I know. [chuckles]
- [chuckles]
[Jose] After getting
to know everybody,
I think I might wanna reignite
my connection with Kelle.
Kelle has been wanting
to see my wild side.
I'm ready to show her...
my wild side.
This is sneaky.
- But I like it.
- This is romantic,
- for where I'm from.
- Aw...
Let's see if this opens.
There you go.
Here you go.
- After you. Mmm-hmm.
- Gracias.
I think I like it better than
my room at the villa.
[Jose] You do?
- [Kelle] Yeah.
- [Jose] Okay.
Having alone time
without any distractions...
will allow us
to loosen up more.
So, tonight is all about
seeing if we can find
that spark again.
[pops]
- [chuckles]
- [Jose] Okay. Okay, cool.
It scared you? [chuckles]
Don't get scared, Kelle.
[Kelle] I knew
it's coming, too.
Senorita Kelle.
[Kelle] Mmm-hmm.
[speaking Spanish]
[chuckles]
For the pleasure and honor
of being here with you.
- Aw. Thank you. Salud.
- Salud.
[Kelle] I would sneak out
with Jose
every day of the week.
I'm definitely seeing
a playful side in Jose.
I'm not used to seeing him
like this.
He always seems so serious
and I feel like I bring...
the younger side of him out.
So risky, but so fun.
[Jose] I mean, when I'm
decided with something,
I just go for it.
So, why me?
Other than the initial
attraction, of course...
you're just...
you're super-positive.
You just have such a very
kind heart and gentle soul.
But I feel like
you have an old soul, too.
- Mmm-hmm.
- So...
- Thank you.
- And I love your mom.
- She's amazing.
- She is amazing.
And she's fun.
What made you...
circle back over here?
So, I didn't know
if we were going to connect...
- [Kelle] Mmm-hmm. Okay.
- initially.
So, I just kept
my mind open...
- Mmm-hmm.
- And...
I really loved just
how spontaneous you were
when you asked me out
on that plan
- for Mushroom Rock.
- Mmm-hmm.
And I really love
how we connected
and we spoke there and...
what I learned
about you and...
what you learned about me
and how...
I opened up with you.
Also, you're very beautiful.
[Kelle] Everything about Jose
is amazing.
Everything.
Obviously, we keep gravitating
back to one another.
[Jose] Hmm.
The fact that Jose is really
stepping up right now
is huge for me.
Like, he's always been
my number one.
[Jose] I love how...
um... with
certain people how...
- I am, you know.
- [Kelle] Mmm-hmm.
And I like to stick around
those people.
So, you're one of those.
Stick around with people
that get the best out of you.
- Yeah.
- And just enjoy...
- I agree.
- Salud for that.
[Kelle] Mmm-hmm. Again...
- Salud.
- Mexicans say Salud
- every single phrase.
- I know... [chuckles]
- I know that...
- So, get used to it, Kelle.
No, I noticed that,
- because your mom does that
all the time.
- All the time.
- [chuckles]
- Yeah. All the time.
We'll do many more of those
for sure.
And many more of these...
Mmm!
[chuckling]
You're being playful, eh?
Come on.
[Jose] I think it was time
to take that next step
of getting to know her.
This night started
with an impulse
and a world of possibilities.
But after this...
it confirmed many things
between her and I.
[Kelle sighs]
- Hola.
- Buenos dias.
- Buenos dias, Senora.
- [chuckles softly]
[Jose] Good morning.
- Morning.
- [glasses clink]
- Did you have fun?
- Amazing.
- You?
- Yeah.
[Kelle] After Billy left me,
I would take
anything with Jose
over anything with Billy
any day.
We had an amazing night
together, for sure.
- Salud.[chuckles]
- Salud to enjoying the moment.
Billy definitely
did me a favor.
Thank you, Billy.
It was good to do this.
- I love it.
- [Kelle] Mmm-hmm.
It's funny that we can see
the house from here, no?
The villa?
[chuckles]
- Yeah, we're not coming back.
- [Kelle] Hola!
- Salud.
- [chuckles]
Salud.
Hi, Pola.
- [chuckles] Hi, Joey.
- [both chuckle]
- Where's my buddy?
- I don't know.
You always know.
- Mmm-hmm.
- He didn't sleep in my room.
Excuse me!
What?
[April] Really, Pola?
[Pola] Jose always tells me
where he's going
and it was weird
that he didn't mention
anything to me,
because we have
a great communication.
He's gonna have
an explanation.
I saw him
sneak out with Kelle.
Are you serious?
[Shannan] To not come back,
that's not him.
I have no words.
I am devastated.
[Ryan]
[Shannan] I should've
came through.
- Where y'all going?
- Where you going?
I don't think it's his type
as well.
I don't see him with her.
Right.
I really cannot believe
Jose chose
Kelle to spend
a night with him.
Like, maybe having a drink.
- Right.
- And dancing on a little bit.
Yes. But Jose is really like
he goes very deep.
- You know.
- I know how he is.
- I know. We have
very thoughtful conversations.
- And I don't know if Kelle
is like that.
- [whispers] Ready?
- [whispers] Yeah.
Oh, I'm definitely
a little bit nervous
going back to the Villa.
[Pola] Like, he's not
gonna come back.
He texted me.
He always tells Mom.
- Just...
- He's right there.
- Where?
- [April] We have questions.
Here he comes.
- Really?
- Yeah. I got
a lot of questions.
- One, two... four moms.
- [April] Jose...
Buenos dias. How are you?
- Ehm... late, bruh.
- [yawns]
I didn't know what's going on.
I'm like...
I couldn't stay there.
I was just heartbroken.
I was crushed.
[both] And where did you
sleep last night?
Just going around.
- [Shannan] Excuse me?
- Going around where?
- Oh, we went around town.
It was cool.
- With who?
- Uh-huh.
- Like, me,
by myself. [chuckles]
- No, you weren't.
- [laughs]
- [Shannan] Tell him...
- [April] Tell him by yourself.
- No, you weren't...
- I don't remember
where I was.
- [Shannan] I saw...
- I sleepwalk.
I saw Kelle
sneak out with you.
Y'all not sleek,
I saw it.
- [April] Jose!
- I saw it. I saw it...
with my own eyes.
- [Jose] Yeah?
- [Shannan] Uh-huh.
[Jose] A relationship
is between two people.
We don't wanna talk
about this with anyone...
'cause it's between
Kelle and Jose.
I don't know. Your stock
went down with me right now.
My stock went down
with you, why?
- Why?
- [Shannan] Yes.
Not cool at all.
[Jose] Mmm-hmm.
It's Kelle's fault that
Jose is not being truthful.
I think that...
whatever they did
the night before...
she's controlling
the situation...
Yeah. He keeps trying
to deflect.
Anybody wants coffee?
You're just popping around
from one to the next?
- What's up with that?
- [Pola] Yeah.
You don't do that.
That's not cool.
If you trying to play me,
it's not gonna work for me.
- Okay. Let's go... oh...
- [Pola] Right now...
You don't want your coffee
before you go?
No, thank you.
- Oh, my God.
- [Shannan] Did somebody
say something?
"Tomorrow, it will be the time
to choose your match.
If your choice is a mismatch,
you could go home."
Ah...
"If your choice is a mismatch,
you could be going home."
What does that mean?
- Why would it be a mismatch?
- If somebody picks you,
but you don't pick them.
[Jimmy] I just wanna
find love.
And I really haven't got
to connect with somebody.
It just isn't working out
with me.
[phone chimes]
"Moms and sons,
we all have dirty laundry
that needs to be addressed.
Today, there's a bin full
of the men's dirty laundry
waiting for the moms.
And one full of the women's
dirty laundry
waiting for the sons.
The mother and son
who correctly identify
the most pieces
of each other's dirty laundry
- will win a special date..."
- Wow.
"Sons, you're up first.
It's time to start sorting."
[laughs boisterously]
- Wow.
- [Stefany] Billy, we got this.
[woman chuckles]
[Joey] I'm kinda grossed out
and I never thought
I'd be doing this
ever in my life,
but here we go.
I'm pretty sure
my dirty laundry
is pretty hot.
- Oh, God...
- [chuckles]
[Jimmy] If you identify
your mom's underwear...
- [all chuckling]
- That's what I'm saying.
You shouldn't know
your mom's underwear.
[Harrison] I'm not
looking forward
- to this.
- Is it just weird,
'cause it's mine, or like...
Uh, it's just weird
in general.
[chuckles]
- Get it!
- Uh!
- All right.
- Let's get to work, boys.
- Oh, man.
Should we go...
This is Ryan's. [chuckles]
Yeah... whoa!
[Jose] My mommy's more
of the sport.
So, it may be this one
for sure.
And this one for sure.
I mean, I worked out
with my mom.
These are kinda sexy, right?
These kinda sexy.
I feel like...
[Jose] So, you did that
thinking it was your mom's?
[all exclaiming]
Your son put that
in the mouth.
- Is that yours?
- [Shannan] Oh,
that's a little small.
- [chuckles]
- No, that ain't mine.
[Gabriel] Ryan definitely
was not funny.
I didn't even think
he came off sexy.
[all cheering]
It was really off-putting.
These look like
double-ds to y'all?
[Jimmy] No, bruh!
Those are Bs.
[Jimmy] Your mom's a D, bro.
- Like, what?
- [chuckles]
I'm like, that's how I know
Joey's a kid still.
He literally has
a B-size bra on.
He's going like, "Yup.
These are my mom's."
It's the other way
around, dude.
[chuckles]
I don't think any of them
are my mom's.
I'm not feeling very confident
in this challenge.
So, wait, wait, wait, wait.
How you go from extra large
- to small, my guy?
- I didn't check
the size on this.
You should've.
I... [chuckles softly]
don't wear underwear.
- Ew.
- [chuckles]
That's so nasty.
Everybody confident
in their pick?
- We're good. Let's go.
- All right.
I'm a little nervous.
I think, you know,
what am I revealing
about like...
You know...[hesitates]
- You...
- [chuckles]
- What are you gonna
find out about me?
- [chuckles]
- It's very strange.
[all exclaiming, cheering]
[all cheering]
- [all cheering]
- [Harrison] Let's go!
[indistinct conversation]
- It's a two?
- This is Billy.
- These are Billy's.
- Did you bought them?
- I did, actually.
- [all laughing]
Oh, my gosh.
I know for a fact,
these are Ryan's.
I know that.
- They're silky.
- [chuckles]
- Feel like your son?
- Maybe.
- Okay.
[chuckles]
[April] Wait a second.
This has to be Harrison's,
- Right?
- [Soyoung] Yes.
Magic Mike.
Hello!
- Is this...
- [Charlene] These
are not Harrison's.
[April] I think
this is Harrison's.
[Harrison] No, that wasn't me.
I never wore like
the thongs or the jockstraps
for stripping...
I always kept it...
classy, with like, some
boxer briefs. [chuckles]
I think these belong
to Harrison's.
These look like
some exotic dancer.
I mean, you can't
keep it classy,
when you're stripping,
but like...
I just wanted to keep it...
comfortable and I just
don't see wearing a thong
being comfortable
at all. [chuckles]
Okay, so, I chose...
these ones, because...
eh... it's something
she should wear at the gym
or she usually
wears at the gym.
All the time.
These ones too.
- Yeah.
- And on a trip, we had our
suitcases mixed up.
- So, when I opened them--
- And you found them there?
It's an emoji on a...
- [Pola] A 100 percent.
- [all cheering]
[Jose] So, I remember...
Pola's underwear
fit her personality.
And it is a bit of a turn on.
- What you see is what you get.
- A little spicy.
Um, I chose these all,
'cause I know my mom's
super-tiny.
I looked in the sizes.
It says "SP". It's like
super-small or something...
-"Small Petite."
- [all cheering]
All of them!
I chose this one, pink one.
- Yup, you got it.
- I thought...
this one was yours, too.
There's one in there
that looks almost the same.
- [buzzer sounds]
- Almost. Right.
[chuckling]
[Ryan] I feel like I've seen
these before.
- Eh...
- Maybe like 15-20 years ago
in the laundry basket somewhere.
[Shannan] I would've
worn those 15-20 years ago.
- I wear those now.
- Ah...
- [chuckles]
- [buzzer sounds]
[Ryan] You would've been
my second choice though.
I did floss with 'em.
I used my smarts to say
she would definitely
bring a set.
So...
- I think I'm good on
all three, eh?
- All three.
- All right.
- [chuckles]
I know my mom's all cutesy
and likes hearts and...
[bleep]
- So...
- [chuckling]
I was like, are these yours?
- Yes.
- [all exclaiming]
I got the one on your hat.
April's underwear game
is strong.
I really didn't expect that
from her.
Because she's really...
such a nice woman.
- [chuckles softly]
- She's got a little fire.
Damn!
[Joey] As I was picking,
you don't really wear bras
and you're more just
out with it, but...
Maybe this could
possibly be yours.
That's definitely mine.
- [Joey] It is!
- [all cheering]
Underwear tells a lot
about a person.
How they feel
about themselves.
Seeing Kelle with...
her choices of underwear...
- [Pola chuckles]
-[Jose] It's...
[Pola] You were
expecting that.
[chuckling]
- [chuckles]
- You were waiting for me
to tell you, though!
No, I was just thinking...
[chuckles]
Kinda picked
the silver surfers,
- but...
- Those are mine.
[all chuckling]
From the beginning, Joey and I
were like, soulmates, so...
it does not surprise me
that he picked my little,
- panties with the bow.
- [retches]
[chuckles softly] I can't.
- Attaboy.
- [dings]
So, I chose these for my son,
Gabriel Jane,
because he is...
an underwear model.
Am I right?
Atta-mama! That's my mama!
[all cheering]
Ooh!
[Shannan] Ryan,
did I get these right?
- [Ryan] It matches.
- [Shannan] Bam!
He's also has a wild side
to him as we all know.
Those are mine!
[all chuckling]
So, I pick these three
for Billy.
I actually purchased them
before we came.
- [all chuckling]
- [Gabriel] Wow.
[all applauding]
[Kelle] Okay, Soyoung.
All right, so, I picked...
four for Jimmy...
There's a Korean one, too.
[all exclaiming]
I have three.
They're exactly the same.
- [all chuckling]
- [woman] Oh, okay.
Very predictable
and consistent.
[Shannan] Black is unassuming
and classic.
Just like Jose.
Did you think
they'd be bigger?
[both chuckle]
- [phone chimes]
-"Congratulations
to our winning duo.
Soyoung and Jimmy."
[all cheering]
[Jimmy] Weirdly, I was like,
thinking to myself,
whoever wins this challenge,
is just really sus,
you know what I mean?
I even told all the guys,
if you know your mom's
underwear, you're a weirdo.
And somehow, I knew
all my mom's underwear.
"You get to pick a date
for one of you.
Take a few minutes
to talk it over."
We are good teamwork.
We like to win, so...
I feel very excited
in the moment.
Um, it definitely
makes us feel
- closer, I guess... yeah.
- A lot closer.
All right, so, we got a date.
What do you think?
You feeling a date tonight?
I mean, I am...
feeling somebody, but like,
at the same time...
I rather, maybe you go out.
I wanna take Jose out again
and see where we go, you know.
But we have this weird
distance feeling,
right after Kelle and him
went out together.
I don't know.
Uh, I think the girl
that I am feeling
is not really feeling me.
So, I don't really wanna
waste a date right now,
until I really, like,
understand more.
You think she's
running away or?
No, I'm feeling Pola,
you know.
You know, we talk about it.
But she's the only one I could
really see myself like...
you know, getting to know,
interested in.
We have similar interests.
The first week in the villa,
Pola and I...
great connection.
I really haven't got to
connect like that again
with somebody.
It just isn't
working out with me
and I just want to find love.
I'm gonna give you a surprise.
- Yeah, you gonna surprise me?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Pola and I, yeah, we've
really, haven't really
been communicating,
I would say,
'cause she's been spending
so much time with Ryan...
Um...
it kind of makes me
a little nervous,
but I still think
I have a good chance,
because I think what we had
was really genuine,
but we'll see...
[Charlene] I think Soyoung
is really good.
I think she's
looking for the guy
who'll put her into place.
I'm having
a hard time finding...
attraction to these moms.
I can't act like...
and fake like,
this is gonna happen.
- Like never gonna happen.
- But listen,
this is what I'm saying...
I don't need you in my ear
telling me
- no different.
- No.
[Jimmy]
[both chuckle]
- [continues indistinctly]
- Yes.
So, what are we gonna do...
- Jimmy?
- Um...
"What are we not going to do?"
That is the real question.
We're gonna experience life.
- We're not gonna do...
- We're gonna experience life.
I'm so glad that
I won this challenge,
"Dirty underwear", even though
it's a little awkward,
you know, I'm really glad
I prevailed,
because it gives me one
last shot with Pola
to go paddle-boarding
and maybe I can win her over.
[continues indistinctly]
[Ryan] Jimmy's taking Pola
on a date.
It kinda sucks in my eyes,
because I'm concerned
that Jimmy might pull
Pola's eyes from me.
All right. Team work.
What I like so much about Pola
is that she is so independent
and just her own person.
Very transparent.
I can tell who she is
and what she likes
just based off of her
everyday movement
and I'm very interested
in the same things...
the gym and the beach
and silence, nature.
She makes me feel very calm.
I've never really had that...
Beautiful spot.
I like how I feel
about Ryan at this moment.
But I'm not a 100 percent.
So, I'm gonna give myself
another opportunity
to meet Jimmy again.
And let's see.
[Jimmy] Yeah.
I think me and Jimmy
have a beautiful connection.
But it has nothing
to do with Ryan.
They're so different
from each other.
But I really, really, really
love spending time
with both of them.
At this moment,
being with Jimmy...
I'm only thinking about Jimmy.
[Jimmy] Yeah, you're
the only person I could ever,
like, in this house I see
myself, you know,
spending time with.
And it was obvious
from the start.
Yeah, I think the reason
I do like you
so much, is because you're...
there's so much to you.
I find Pola
the most beautiful
and interesting person here.
It's honestly clear to em
when I think in my head,
Pola's very interested.
But at the same time...
she's keeping her options.
I know what Pola likes.
And I know what Ryan likes.
And those Lego pieces
just don't really fit.
So, why did you choose me?
You know that saying,
it's like, I'm in a room
full of people,
but there's
nobody truly there.
- That's true.
- And it's like
everywhere I go,
I feel like
there's nobody there,
but when I'm with you,
I feel like
there's somebody that's
in there that, like,
- you know, that exists.
- Mmm-hm.
You don't need
to explain anymore.
I understand.
I feel the same way.
[Jimmy] I feel really good
about Pola right now.
She makes me feel lost
in the moments
and I think
that's really important
in any relationship.
I've never really had that.
Never had somebody just...
allow me to escape
from everything.
But let me do something.
Just lay down on your back.
- Mmm-hmm.
- And close your eyes.
- Oh my back? Okay.
- Yeah.
- [Pola] Mmm.
- [Jimmy] Mmm.
[exhales]
[Pola] I really feel that
Jimmy is really sensual...
and that's part of why
I like to be around him.
That feels so nice...
[Pola]
[Jimmy] The water
starts to just
swell in and out
through the sand.
You can feel it
dripping on you.
And it was very sensual and...
relaxing at the same time, I...
you know, I'm glad like...
I didn't get a boner
or anything.
[Pola] He has so much to give.
And I love
sharing time with him.
I feel Ryan is more
fun to be around.
But I really feel like
I have a great connection
with Jimmy.
We are really
seeing each other
and listening to each other.
He makes me feel
really special
when I'm around him. He does.
- Mmm.
- So, you owe me a massage.
I owe you everything.
- Salud.
- I owe you the world.
- [phone chimes]
- [Pola] Hey!
I got a text!
"The connection between
a mother and a son
brought you to the villa..."
[Charlene] Mmm...
[Pola] "But to stay...
you need to have formed
a new romantic one."
[all exclaiming]
"Tomorrow, it will be the time
to choose your match."
- [women chuckling]
- [all exclaiming]
[Pola] "If the feeling
is mutual,
you will continue with
this journey as a new pair.
However...
if your choice is a mismatch,
you could be going home."
[all exclaiming]
[Ryan] I'm a bit shellshocked
at this point.
Because...
that's a lot of pressure,
I think, on a lot of people
in the house.
Yeah...
[Pola] I feel stressed,
because I'm close to Ryan
and Jimmy.
So, if I have to pick
either one of them,
that is a little bit scary.
"If your choices
are mismatched,
you could be going home."
What does that mean?
- Why would it be a mismatch?
- Like, if somebody picks you,
but you don't pick them.
[Jimmy] I would say that
I'm definitely here
to experience love, find love.
And I think, with time,
you know,
Pola could possibly
be that person for me,
and hopefully,
I could possibly
be that person for her.
Yeah, I'm really
not connecting with anybody
on the villa.
I got a lot to think about
right now.
And I don't really wanna
fake anything.
[Charlene] I think Soyoung
is really good.
You gotta just step up
to the plate and be a man.
What would the man in you...
who would you like?
If it's Soyoung,
you gotta make a move
and get in there.
I'm getting on
Harrison's case,
because after the text,
I don't want him to go home.
This retreat is all about
making that romantic love...
connection.
I think she's looking
for the guy
to put her in the place.
That's an opportunity
for you to put on
the man-pants,
because guess what?
That's never gonna go away.
Women are always
gonna want that.
We're always gonna
want that man,
who can take charge
in the bedroom.
I need a man.
I need a man to be a man.
And these women who're like,
"I wanna be
in-charge and all",
that's like cool sometimes.
But if that's like your MO,
like that's not normal.
But if I go in the bedroom
with you
and that's what
you're expecting,
then why don't
I just be a lesbian?
Why don't I just go
get a strap on
and be with another woman?
Why would I be with a man?
I want you to step up
to the plate, okay?
I just would like if you could
do that for me, Harrison.
You're picking up
what I'm putting down, huh?
Bro, all you do is just...
- talk, bro.
- [chuckles nervously]
Well, because what I'm saying
is valuable information.
Will you pray about
what I'm saying?
- No, I will not.
- What?
[Harrison] Basically, my mom
wants the best for me
for dating.
I feel like my mom's like...
my whole life, has always been
like a coach on the sideline,
like, always coaching me up
and just trying
to talk me through it and...
just push through it,
get through it.
Having her there on
the sideline, like as a coach,
she has to know
when to, like, pull back
when enough is enough.
Tell me why you couldn't see
her being able to turn you on.
I can't act like and fake like
this is gonna happen...
- It's never gonna happen.
- But listen, this is what
I'm saying...
- And I don't need you in my
ear telling me no different.
- No.
I'm having a hard time
finding an attraction
to these moms...
They're a lot older than me.
Yeah, they're
pretty and stuff,
but I'm just not really...
attracted to them.
Hey, I agree with you.
- I...
- Please don't get close to me.
- You know... like...
- You know what I mean.
Okay, well, I agree with you,
'cause it's an experiment.
And sometimes,
with an experiment,
means we try something.
- Trials and failures.
- Great! So, it's totally fine!
[Charlene] Me and Harrison,
definitely butt heads
once in a while
and especially,
if I'm challenging him...
you know, to sync
outside of his comfort zone...
it can be an issue
and that's what I'm doing.
- Any other reason?
- I don't know, you tell me!
Like, you keep hammering me.
Do you know how to zip it?
- [Charlene] Well, because I...
- Please,
- 'cause sometimes
you know how to talk--
- I wanna hear from you more.
I know! I'm done talking!
[Charlene] Well, tell us more!
I'm done talking, bruh.
[sighs]
Bro, all she does
is just talk.
I'm so over it.
[Harrison] Coming
into the villa,
I was expecting to maybe,
you know, find love or...
you know, find a relationship,
But it's just not
what I expected.
I had, like, an open mind.
I was willing to try
different things...
you know, stick around
and see through, but...
I just couldn't really
connect with the moms
in that kinda romantic level.
So, I got something
to say to you.
Tell me.
I'm really proud of you,
for, you know, opening up
and being yourself and...
You know, it was really cool
for me to see that of you,
but for me...
I wanna have to tell you,
this is where my journey...
is gonna come to a stop.
- Um...
- Like, are you...
are you sure?
That's what I mean.
There's not really, like...
one person here that
I kinda like...
- hold on to--
- Like, not Soyoung? Not...
- No.
- In the sauna, in the gym...
working out, not in... just...
- Not really.
- You're good? No?
- Yeah.
- I was thinking that
Harrison was missing out,
because he wasn't getting
in touch with that
romantic, vulnerable side,
like, opening himself up
to a woman,
even if it's not like,
they're gonna fall in love.
But he's also set
in his principles
and it's kind of like,
why would you even go there,
if there's
not a real possibility?
If you know that,
then it's fine.
I love you and I'm
super-proud of you
- for being...
- Yeah.
- true to yourself.
- Mmm-hmm.
- And you know... yeah.
- Staying true is all I can do.
That's it.
- Yeah.
- It's the only thing
we can do.
I really respect Harrison
for wanting to go home
and I'm really proud of him
and I understand...
you know, the courage
and the decency
that it takes for him
to stand on his principles
and be firm
and not lead anybody on.
I gotta say goodbye.
- I'm leaving.
- [Gabriel] Why
are you leaving?
Why?
You know, I haven't really
connected with
anybody, like...
on that level.
You know, you guys have always
got a place in my heart,
you know... I will always
remember your guys
- and... cherish...
- [April] Mmm-hmm.
[Charlene] We'll always
have Mexico.
We'll always have Mexico...
La Paz.
- [chuckles softly]
- You did amazing, you know?
Yeah, I learned a lot here,
you know?
Harrison is a great guy,
I think...
you know, this whole dynamic
of dating older kinda
threw him for a loop.
So, I totally see...
how, you know,
he made that choice
and I respect him for it,
you know.
God let him
out of here. [chuckles]
- [Harrison] Good bye, Pola.
- [Pola] Take care.
I'm really gonna miss you.
Right, you too.
- Goodbye, Jose.
- Oh...
[Jose]
You're special, brother.
- Yeah, true.
- Thank you...
Hi, Kelle.
Once I got to the villa
and like, realized...
what the situation
was gonna be,
I really didn't wanna stay,
but I stayed true
to my principles.
Stood true
in what I believed in.
And through that, I feel like
my mom and I...
we got a little closer
and we grew.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
- [Harrison] Have a good time.
- [Charlene] See you soon.
[Harrison] And
no holding back.
You know, I just wanted
to see her fall in love.
She deserves it.
It's been a long time
and I just wanna
see her happy.
[Charlene] Is there a guy
out there for me or what?
Anything's possible
at this point.
Anything is possible. Right.
Harrison's just
left because...
he wasn't feeling
a connection with anyone.
However, there's someone
I wanna get to know better.
And I'm just gonna go for it.
You know, I came here
hoping to find love and...
[clicks tongue] You know...
I'm really hoping
I can make that happen.
I really wanna get to know
Charlene a little bit better.
Because, you know,
she's so down to earth,
and sweet and you know...
kind of intellectual, so...
I'm hoping I can use
the rest of my time here
to make a connection
with Charlene.
I was wondering if maybe
you wanted to take a...
walk around
this cactus garden here.
- That'd be great... Thank you.
- Yeah.
[Ryan S chuckles softly]
There's a couple of things
that are pretty interesting,
you know...
not all cacti are green,
for example.
- Um...
- Right.
There're some that are...
purplish, reddish, yellowish.
Here? That are here?
- Uh...
- That you've seen
or you just...
Oh, look. Here's purple.
[Ryan S] Yeah. Here's
a purple one.
- [chuckles nervously]
- [Charlene] This is purple.
I'm blown away by the size
of all these...
Yeah. It's kind of incredible.
They only grow
one inch, a year.
[Charlene] Really?
I definitely hope that Ryan
grows faster than a cactus.
[chuckles]
So, some of these
really tall ones...
there're some at least
ten feet tall here,
they must be over
a 100-years-old.
These are called
the elephant tree.
- Okay.
- Um... in the genus Procera.
The Native Americans actually
use the sap from this...
the red sap, as a way to heal
skin conditions.
[Charlene] I did not know
I was going on a cactus date
and I'm thinking, aren't you
a software engineer?
How do know all this stuff
about cactuses?
- Wow! Look at this.
- Well, I have...
this ceviche.
[Charlene] Very nice.
I've noticed you drink coffee
pretty often.
- So, might join you though.
- Yeah, pretty often. [giggles]
[Charlene] I really enjoy
that Ryan took the time
to create a day and a setting
that would...
impress me,
but also make me
feel comfortable
and I'm totally...
feeling special.
So, tell me a little bit
more about
what makes you tick.
- You know... what drives you?
- Oh, nice!
Well, I like that...
the fact that you asked me
what drives me.
I'm finding myself like...
a little attracted to you
and I think that there's...
you know... thank you...
something there, 'cause I was
like... [chuckles softly]
- we haven't really...
- Yeah.
[Charlene] I like Ryan and...
you know, we're out
under the stars.
If we're gonna test the waters
and see if there's
anything here...
This will be a good time
for a kiss, you know,
because then we'll know.
- You like avocado?
- I love avocado.
Everything in here, the onion,
you're good with?
- [Ryan S] Oh, yeah.
- So, it's fair,
we both have...
- Yeah...
- We'll both have onion breath.
[chuckles softly]
You see me struggling there?
That's me thinking
about the kiss.
- [chuckles]
- [chuckles nervously]
I think Charlene might wanna
kiss tonight.
Feeling kinda nervous
about this.
Takes a little while for me
to sort of, like...
you know, take my armor off
and get intimate with someone.
Um...
Do you wanna walk over to,
maybe, the beach side?
You know, look at the beach,
maybe find the moon somewhere?
Okay, that would be awesome.
I...
still kinda need
to feel this out.
[Charlene] How did your hand
get so cold?
[Ryan S] Um...
I think you are
a magnificent woman.
It is really difficult for me
to choose between
Ryan and Jimmy.
I really makes me not know
what to do.
[sighs in exasperation]
[Ryan] Jimmy's already
had his time with Pola.
I feel like Pola's the person
for me.
I feel like we've had
the deepest bond,
doing this experience and...
I'm literally putting it
on the line tonight.
I'm about to go hard.
Where are we going?
I don't know.
[Pola] So, right now,
I'm a little bit confused...
because I had a great time
with Jimmy
and I'm expecting
to have a great time
with Ryan as well.
I really like them both.
They're so different,
one from the other one.
It's really complex,
what I feel.
But I don't wanna hurt
anybody's feelings.
So, hopefully Ryan's date
will help me make up my mind.
Oh, my God.
This is beautiful.
- [Ryan] You like it?
- [Pola] Yes.
- [Ryan] Really?
- [Pola] Thank you so much.
[Ryan] I'm glad you like it.
Let's eat. Let's take a seat.
I think Ryan is really
special because...
he thought a lot
about this date...
and he made everything
so perfect.
And that's something
that really makes me happy.
Oh, my God. This is beautiful.
You know?
How can you beat that, right?
I haven't taken the time.
But if you wanna
paint the moon...
[chuckles softly]
...I did bring a canvas
along with me.
[both chuckling]
- [chuckles]
- So, we can look right here.
- Okay...
- And this little picture...
- and we can paint the moon.
- Are you a good painter?
It doesn't matter.
- Okay... yeah.
- I'mma be honest,
we gonna do it together.
But I know how much...
you're into your hi-fives...
Out of all of your dates
so far...
This has been really good.
- This has been good.
- I like this...
- Don't give the "friend hand"
on a date.
- [chuckles]
Don't you "Jimmy" me.
- So, we should fingerpaint.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah...
- 'Cause I know...
how much you like
your hi-fives.
- I like that.
- So, we can...
eat some food
if you want to...
But if you don't wanna
do that yet...
No, let's do that first.
- You wanna paint?
- Yeah.
[Pola] It's really weird
that Ryan sees
how I always go like,
hi-five with everyone.
He tells me things that
he sees about me...
that makes me really happy
that he observes so much.
You can do this side
and I'll do this side, okay?
- And let's see...
- And then we gotta
put them together? Okay.
- Is this still my side or not?
- Uh-huh.
This is your side.
[Ryan] I like that.
- You're pretty good with this.
- You're good, right?
You're actually pretty good
with this, so...
I'm enjoying
my time here, actually.
I don't wanna go.
Not now. I don't wanna leave.
- Then don't leave.
- No, I'm not gonna leave.
- Stay here with me.
- I am.
Stay here with me.
[Ryan] My connection with Pola
is just special
and unique to me...
because I probably
never met a woman...
in my life, aside from my mom,
who's so elegant and humble,
but confident...
at the same time.
And that's something
that I admire.
So, creative activity
number two...
So, what I attempted to do
is this...
I started to make a song
for you...
And what I did was...
This is so exciting.
I attempted to translate it
to Spanish.
Okay, let's do that.
First line, it's...
Flaws and all
[chuckles softly]
I want you
Just the way you are
[vocalizing]
Let down your walls
[singing in Spanish]
- How was it?
- Good.
- It's good?
- Yeah. Great.
- Are you just saying that
it's good?
- You did good.
- All right. Thank you.
- Who helped you with that?
Nobody.
- You made it really special.
- Thank you
for being my really
special date.
Thank you for being
really special...
[Ryan] The biggest thing
for me at this point
between me and Pola,
is the fact that...
her guard began to come down.
I think there's a love there
and a chemistry.
And I like where it's going.
- I love your company.
- Thank you.
I think you are a magnificent
and exquisite woman.
- Thank you so much.
- And I am looking forward
to learning
all of the best parts of you.
And I know you have many...
because I've already seen
so many great sides to you.
So, thank you.
[Pola] I feel I'm really happy
with Ryan
because he makes
everything really special
and he wrote a song to me.
It's the first time that
anybody writes a song to me.
It really makes me...
not know what to do.
It is really difficult for me
to choose between
Ryan and Jimmy.
[sighs in exasperation]
"Let's see what your friends
and family
have to say about
your new relationship."
I am hoping it is not
any of my exes.
- Oh, my Lord!
- Come here.
[shrieks]
Am I being pranked right now?
[Jose] Your mom has become
someone very special for me.
If I asked you to go
on a date with me,
would you?
Okay... [chuckles]
- You have beautiful eyes.
- Thank you. You as well.
I love me some beautiful,
brown eyes, you know...
So, you'd be down to know me?
[Joey] What did I just
get myself into?
Like, holy [bleep]
"The time has come to see
if you found a match..."
"Text the name of the person
you want to continue
your journey with here..."
"However, if your choice
is a mismatch..."
"You will be leaving
the villa today..."
- Wow!
- This is gonna be tough.
[Jose] I'm in a very
difficult position.
I have found
chemistry with
several of them.
And it's breaking my heart.
[sighs]