[narrator]
Previously on Milf Manor...
Everywhere I go, I feel like
there's nobody there.
But when I'm with you,
I feel like there's somebody
that's in there that like,
you know, that exists.
I understand.
I feel the same way.
[Jimmy] I feel really good
about Pola right now.
She makes me feel lost
in the moments.
And I think
that's really important.
I've never really had that.
It feels so nice with her.
[Pola] I've a great connection
with Jimmy.
He makes me feel
really special
when I'm around him.
He does.
- [Ryan] I love your company.
- [Pola] Thank you.
I think you are a magnificent
and exquisite woman.
I feel like Pola
is the person for me
because I probably never met
a woman who is so elegant
and humble.
And that's something
that I admire.
- [Pola] I don't want
to go from here.
- Then don't leave.
- No, I'm not gonna leave.
- Stay here with me.
[Pola] I feel I'm really happy
with Ryan
because he makes everything
really special.
And it's really difficult
for me
to choose between
Ryan and Jimmy.
Argh!
You're really special.
- You're special.
- Thank you.
Jose gives me lots of
butterflies, get nervous,
and I get giggle,
and I don't know what to do.
Mwah!
How do you feel when you see
the exterior of me?
I'm gonna say your elegance.
That's hot. I like Jose.
He's my one and only.
He has my attention.
[Pola]
Jose is not in my room.
I have no idea why.
Like, I try to text him,
but I haven't had any answer.
And that's really weird.
- Here we are.
- Thank you.
We are enjoying
this beautiful moment.
The fact that Jose is really
stepping up right now
is huge for me.
Like, he's always been
my number one.
Everything about Jose
is amazing.
He didn't sleep in my room.
Excuse me. I have no words.
I am devastated.
Tomorrow, it will be the time
to choose your match.
If your choice is a mismatch,
you could go home.
[Ryan] I'm a bit
shell shocked.
That's a lot of pressure.
Yeah.
That is a little bit scary.
Oh, I got a text, Gabriel.
Hold on.
The time has come to see
if you found a match.
Text the name of the person
you want to
continue your journey
with here, if you have one.
If the feeling is mutual,
you will stay in the villa.
However,
if your choice is a mismatch
or you don't enter a name...
...you will be
leaving the villa today.
Wow.
So enter your matches
name now.
We need to select who we have
the strongest connection with,
with the hopes that
that person feels the same.
So what are we doing?
From day one, my connection's
always been more so with Jose.
So I'm... I'm texting Jose.
- I'm going with that.
- Okay.
I know that
we have a connection.
However, you know,
he did not ask me out.
I mean, Pola went on a date
with Jimmy, too, so.
[Shannan] That's true.
Despite the fact that Jose
has snuck out with Kelle,
I still believe in me
and I still know
the thoughtful conversations
and connection that
he and I share,
which that
in itself is special.
I got to believe that
real connection
will supersede
and intrigue every day.
I got a whole fun
and believing in that.
- Regardless, you know
I'm here for you.
- I know.
- So are you, my baby.
- [Ryan] There we go.
I'm proud of my mom
going for what she wants,
but I'm not necessarily
so sure if Jose
will pick my mom.
And that concerns me
a little bit.
It does.
Oh, this is getting wild.
Yeah.
I'm going all the way.
I'm... I'm not just,
like, playing games.
- I'll go with my feelings.
- Yeah, go with your feelings.
- And that's real,
trust me, so.
- Yeah.
Even though I knew that Kelle
and Jose have a connection,
I just go with Jose
because I don't want to
just play game.
I want to show that
that's real.
I still have that little hope
that Jose will pick me.
Yep.
Love you.
[Jose]
So let's see what happens
with these matches
and where we're
going from here.
This is gonna be tough.
This is gonna be
very emotional
because of all the people that
I've done strong
connections with.
So to make the decision,
I'm trusting my gut
and my feelings.
And those feelings
are pointing
towards one person.
I'm between
two different names,
but one of them,
I feel like the connection
more as a friendship.
And the other one
is more like,
uh, maybe there's a feud.
- [Jose] Possibility.
- Yeah.
I really don't know what to do
because I really love
the company of Ryan and Jimmy.
Uh,
they're completely different,
I understand.
And I don't want to
hurt anyone's feelings.
Obviously,
you have to pick one.
I mean, you have to
make a decision.
You cannot stay
with both of them.
So...
I'm gonna write...
I'm gonna send it.
Wow.
Yeah.
I guess I have
to do the same.
I really think the best match
for Jose is Shannon, 100%.
I don't feel Kelle
is right for Jose.
I really don't.
I think it's very important
for me that my mom sees
what I see in the woman
that I choose.
Because when you're
with someone,
you're not only
with that person,
you're with that
person's circle.
And having those people accept
and have a good relationship
with your significant other,
it brings a lot of peace
and value...
- I feel the same way
with Jose.
- ...in the relationship.
I'm sure whoever leaves,
they're gonna have
good memories
from you and me,
and that's something
that I really like.
[Gabriel] This whole thing,
it just,
is kind of making it so real.
And I have to make
a decision now.
You know, it's kind of scary.
It's making me have
butterflies in my stomach.
[Charlene] I picked Ryan
as for my connection,
and I think that we have
something to build off of.
So people are going home today
and I am not thinking
that it's going to be me.
[Kelle] I'm a little concerned
that maybe my connection
with Jose isn't as strong
as his with somebody else,
but I don't know
what his relationships
look like with the other woman
in the villa.
I only know how ours are
and how he makes me feel
when we're together.
I feel like we have
the strongest connection here.
If Jose doesn't pick me,
I would be shocked.
And if he picks Shannan,
I'll be pissed, absolutely.
[phone vibrates]
I got a text.
Oh, boy.
Oh-oh.
[woman] Here we go.
"Congratulations."
You have a match.
You and Stefany
chose each other.
You're both staying
to explore your connections.
- [woman] Yay!
- Yay!
[indistinct]
- I'm so happy.
- Yay!
This feels so amazing
right now to know that
we both chose each other,
and it could potentially
be something solid.
- So I get your approval?
- You have my approval.
I came here to find the one,
and I feel that Gabriel
could potentially be the one.
- Do you approve?
- I do.
[all cheering]
[phone vibrates]
I got a text.
Oh, it's so dramatic.
I feel it.
Oh, my God.
[indistinct]
Really?
Come, come, come.
I needed to make a decision,
but it wasn't easy,
and it's still not easy.
Jimmy and Ryan both chose you
for their match.
Who did you choose?
[Jimmy] I find Pola absolutely
beautiful inside and out.
I know from the time
that I've spent with Pola,
she is a person
that I would be interested
in on the outside world.
And I'm just hoping
that she feels
the same way about me.
I really like Pola's spirit.
Just the fact like,
like she is so open.
I think me and Pola
are building a romance.
I think it's becoming
more physical day by day.
I think she's more comfortable
with me day by day.
So I think Pola and Jimmy
have a different type
of connection.
But I will say
there's always that
small piece of doubt
that creeps into your head.
I'm not really
a nervous person,
but it's kind of
nerve-wracking
just waiting for that answer,
for that yes or no.
You're like, did I do enough?
You know, do you really
feel the way I feel about you?
I feel so stressed.
I don't want to be
the one
who tells
who will leave the villa.
This is so hard.
Jimmy and Ryan both chose you
for their match.
Who did you choose?
Can they both stay?
Please.
[Jimmy]
Mamma, are you sad too?
[Soyoung] Oh, she's crying.
She's crying.
Don't cry.
[Ryan] All right.
Like, Jesus, I am really close
to your moms, both of them.
And I don't want you
to feel like
I've been betraying
our friendship
because I'm not.
- No, no.
- So, Ryan, I chose you.
[cheering]
[Shannan] I'm glad that Pola
had enough common sense
to make the right choice.
[Ryan]
I do see a future with her.
I think the patience,
time and energy
that we put into
each other is paying off.
Pola allows me
to be my true self.
[Ryan speaking]
Yeah.
[Pola] Sorry.
[Jimmy] Don't be sorry.
[Pola] It really hurt me
saying to Jimmy
that I chose Ryan.
I really enjoyed his company
and it was really painful.
But I chose Ryan
because of the last date.
It was so special about
the painting and the song.
[phone vibrates]
[sighs]
Charlene,
you chose Ryan as...
as your match,
but he did not choose you.
I'm a little bummed that
I didn't get a real connection
with anybody here in La Paz.
Maybe I'm a little pushy
and a little intense
for the guys.
I don't know.
I didn't expect a home run,
but I was hoping to make
a couple of base hits here.
Since you and Ryan S
did not make a match,
you will be leaving the villa.
[woman] I'm sorry.
[Harrison]
I considered putting
in Charlene,
but I don't see much of
a romantic connection there.
- [phone vibrates]
- [bleep] I got a text.
[women] Okay.
Congratulations.
You and April
chose each other.
Oh!
You are both staying to
explore your connections.
[indistinct]
[April] Joey.
- I'm keeping my eye on you.
- I know. I know.
[cheering]
Whoa!
You scared me.
[Joey]
I'm just very happy that
I picked her
and she picked me.
We get to stay.
I more than approve.
[Gabriel]
I feel like it's alarming.
And I'm annoyed right now
because I don't
really want my mom
dating a little kid
because she's, like,
such a smart,
experienced woman.
And I just feel like,
can a kid really suffice?
Like her needs?
I don't know.
[phone vibrates]
I have a text.
Jose,
Kelle, Soyoung and Shannan,
all chose you for their match.
who do you choose?
Jose is the heartthrob
of the villa.
He's beautiful to look at.
He's amazing.
You know,
he has a great personality.
For me, Jose is my number
one pick, my only pick.
I feel that I am falling
for Jose
and he's exactly
what I'm looking for.
So mature
and romantic and loving.
Though I'm feeling
very confident,
I'm not really sure
where his head's at.
I just want to hear my name,
that's all.
[Soyoung] Here we are.
And three women
and it was unexpected.
I'm hoping that
I have a little chance.
The woman that I chose...
is Kelle.
[woman] Oh, Kelle.
Thank you.
I am so excited
that Jose picked me.
[Joey] I knew that he would
make the right choice
in the back of my mind.
But if he made
a out of pocket wrong choice,
then me and Jose
wouldn't have been cool.
But he made the right choice.
So we're cool.
[Shannan] It's all good.
No worries.
I don't want to cry.
I feel like I have been
sucker punched.
Someone has hit me
with a truck.
But it's okay.
I'm gonna always roll with.
That might be for now,
but it won't be for always.
[sobbing]
[Soyoung] I'm very sad.
Actually,
I'm upset with Jose
because I feel like
he betrayed me.
That really hurt me.
[Jimmy] Um-hmm.
Like,
I didn't expect that at all.
[Jose] Seeing Soyoung
and Shannan leave,
it really breaks my heart.
Especially knowing that
it was because of me.
I... I didn't think it was
gonna happen this way.
I know. I know, right.
[Pola] I really cannot believe
Jose choose Kelle
and I'm not happy with that.
I don't see them
together outside the villa.
[phone vibrates]
[Ryan] I got a text.
Ryan S, Billy,
Jimmy,
Soyoung,
Lisa, Shannan
and Charlene.
Unfortunately,
you did not make
a connection.
It's time to pack your bags
and say your goodbyes.
Oh!
[women] Oh, yes!
Yes. Yes. Yes.
[Stefany] Oh, no, Billy.
Yeah.
[Billy] Although
I'm leaving the villa,
I'm stoked for my mom
and Gabriel.
I think they could definitely
have a future with each other.
- See you at home.
- All right.
- See you soon.
- [indistinct]
I'll see you later.
Hopefully the next time
I see her,
she might be in love.
Thank you. Yeah.
We'll see.
- Take care.
- Bye. Bye, Kelle.
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, too.
I'm a little bummed
that Billy is leaving here
without finding love.
I'm definitely
gonna miss him.
Bye.
[Pola speaking
in foreign language]
Although I didn't match
with anyone,
I've learned a lot.
I've learned to come out
of my shell,
and I'm leaving happy.
- [Jose] Bye, Billy.
- [Pola] Good bye.
I will miss Pola, though.
Yeah, she's incredible.
[Soyoung] Mm-hmm.
I don't have a regret.
I will do
it a little differently.
Jose, last minute.
[Jimmy] Nothing I would have
done differently from day one,
and was truly myself.
- It's been a great experience.
- Oh, man.
I think I would have just go
for the Jose
right away
and show my emotions.
I want you to find...
No, I mean,
we always want to find
a love, the true love.
But I hope you find it soon.
- Love you.
- [women] Bye!
Bye, bye.
I came looking for love,
which I found.
You know,
I fell in love within my mom
and love within
all of these people
and friends that I made.
[Pola] What a gorgeous
woman, always.
- Looking...
- Thank you.
[indistinct]
Ryan and I have
always been close.
He's my firstborn,
but I would say
this experience with him
has definitely taken
our relationship
to another level.
Let me know
if you need something.
I got you.
I'm gonna check on you.
- All right?
- I'm very proud of you.
Love you.
- Oh.
- You're still my baby.
But, but, you know,
I respect you as a young man.
Exactly.
And I... I think
we've become better friends,
and that's...
- Yeah.
- ...thus be it.
[Charlene] This is a once
in a lifetime, right?
- [Kelle] That's right.
- We'll always have La Paz.
- Aren't you glad you did it?
- Yes.
- [Pola] Me too.
- Big group hug.
- Yeah.
- [Pola] Give me a hug.
- Big group hug.
- [Kelle] I love you.
- [Charlene] I love you.
Thank you.
[woman]
Give Harrison our love.
- [Charlene] Yeah.
- [Pola] They're family.
[Charlene]
I came here to find love,
but I found more love
for myself.
- [Stefany] Bye, Charlene.
- Bye.
Thank you, guys.
Have fun.
And I've learned that
love can grow
anywhere you will allow it.
And especially if you open
yourself up to new ideas.
Down to us.
Yeah, that's everyone.
Oh, my Lord.
- Come here, baby doll.
- What are you doing?
- How are you?
- [man speaking]
Wow.
- [Kelle speaking]
- [man speaking]
What's happening?
Is this guy actually serious?
[man speaking]
- Beachy girl look...
- Yeah.
...with her cowboy boots on.
I like it.
Beach reminded me of Mexico.
[Jose] This is a nice place,
nice spot.
Yeah.
Gonna have a nice lunch.
[Joey]
It feels a little bit weird
now that half
the house is gone.
So it's going to take
some getting used to.
I'm glad.
- You're glad?
- Yeah.
I'm glad that the people
are gone,
so I can really get to know
Jose more
and connect one on one
without all these distractions.
I mean,
this is what I came here for.
- Yeah.
- And so, you know.
- Quite.
Salud, for sure.
[phone vibrates]
I got a text.
Woo! Okay.
What does it say?
It says, what happens
at the villa,
stay at the villa?
Yeah. What does that mean?
Couples, it's time
to take your connection
into the real world.
A close friend
or family member
will meet you here.
What?
Let's see what your friends
and family have to say
about your new relationship.
Good luck.
Oh!
Oh, no.
I've no idea who's coming.
Do you?
Oh, no.
I thought we were gonna
stay like this forever
in our own little...
I know, in our own
little La Paz bubble.
I like it like that.
I wonder if for us
to continue together,
if they have to approve.
I wonder.
[Ryan] I'm kind of anxious.
I'm anxious to see
who's coming.
I am hoping that
it's not her ex-husband.
[chuckles]
Okay.
So I'm thinking it might be
your, like, best friend
or it might be, I don't know.
Maybe your mom.
Maybe Billy's aunt.
I have no clue.
[Stefany]
A visitor is coming.
I have no idea who it is.
I'm just a little worried
that if this person comes
and meets Gabriel
that they might
not approve of it.
He's a rock star.
They probably think
he's not gonna
take me serious.
So I'm a little nervous.
I am hoping
it is not any of my exes.
I don't think my exes
would approve of me
dating anyone younger.
Do you have any idea
who it might be?
I hope it's McKenna.
Your daughter?
That would be amazing.
It will be such a pleasure meeting.
Yeah.
I'm like shaking.
McKenna is my oldest daughter
of six beautiful kids, and...
Yeah.
McKenna is definitely
my bestie.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
That's my sister.
My sister McKenna,
a.k.a. Disco Bunny.
Her nickname
that she likes to go by
because she choose that,
she likes to dance
and she's really energetic.
My mom, Disco Bunny
and Disco Mommy are like,
exactly the same.
They're like printouts
of each other.
Is this seat taken?
[screams]
Hi, Joey.
Hi, McKenna.
I know, I know, I know.
I think it's a very big deal
that Jose and my sister
get along,
because if they don't,
I mean, my sister
is so close to my mom
that I think she would
kind of drive him out.
If McKenna doesn't
like Jose, he out.
- Bye.
- Yeah.
- All right.
- Yeah, I know.
I always listen to my kids.
They're smarter than me.
- Meet my little friend.
- You must be McKenna.
- Yeah.
- [Kelle] Meet my
little friend.
How are you?
- Come here.
- Pleased to meet you.
Oh, yeah!
No.
Oh, my God.
I'm so happy.
You're gonna make me cry.
I love her.
I'm so happy you came.
Peace is a friend.
We talk all the time.
She has always been there
for me during hard times.
She is someone that I call
to kind of just ask her
to give me tips or give me
a little bit of advice
on the guy that I'm dating.
She's been a support system
in my dating life.
I love her dearly.
Oh, my God.
Voila!
[Pola speaking
in foreign language]
[Emma speaking
[Pola] This amazing
sunshine up here,
it's my daughter, Emma.
I'm so happy
that she's here.
For me, the most
important part
of having a partner
is meeting my kids.
I usually never introduce
my man to my family
unless I feel there's future.
My only concern about
Ryan and Emma meeting
is about Emma liking Ryan.
She is not easy.
Your name is Ryan?
Yes.
So who are you, Ryan?
Someone's coming.
- Somebody is coming?
- Huh.
Oh, my Lord.
- Come here, baby doll.
- What are you doing?
How are you?
[Billy]
I love you so much.
Love you too.
- Hey, I'm Billy.
- I'm Joey.
Nice to meet you.
Billy Jayne is my ex-husband
and Gabriel's father.
I met Billy doing a movie
with him, and I was engaged
at the time,
and he walked
into my dressing room
and took my engagement
ring off.
So that's what he thinks
about other men with me.
How are you doing?
You good?
[Billy] Yeah.
I was with Billy for 17 years,
and we were married for nine.
We divorced around 2003.
Come.
Where?
Home.
- I'm not going.
- All right.
I'm not going home right now.
We're growing
in different directions
and I just wanted to explore
some time
being on my own as a woman.
Enough. Come on.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
- [Billy speaking]
- What's happening?
- I'm supposed to be on...
Ah!
Is this guy actually serious?
Like, is this...
am I being pranked right now?
I thought it was like,
all a joke.
[Billy speaking]
- [April] Oh, okay.
- [Billy speaking]
What are you trying
to prove, bro?
It's just rude,
immature behavior.
My whole crotch is showing.
[Jose]
It's so ungentleman like.
It's something
that you just don't do.
Do you have children?
- No.
- Do you want children?
Um, one day.
Because my mom
doesn't want
any more children.
You know, the throw me
against the wall,
make out with me
anywhere connection.
If I asked you to go
on a date with me, would you?
- [Billy speaking]
- [April speaking]
[Billy speaking]
Don't be fun.
I've been divorced
from Billy for a long time,
but there's definitely
still love
between Billy and I.
So, you know, he's gonna
make his move here and there,
and I'm going with it.
It's my ex-husband.
You know, I go with the flow.
Sit down.
Billy, stay in your lane.
That's my son.
My friend...
[speaking foreign language]
My friend.
Wow.
Oh, look how fast.
Whenever I get
put in awkward situations,
I tend to laugh
and smile
because I don't
really know what to do.
Get mad, start punching them?
No, it's all good.
Obviously, I don't want
to show him, you know,
that it pissed me off
a little bit
because that's just gonna add
more fuel to the fire
with the person like that.
What's your name?
- Jo... Joey.
- Joey.
- Joey. That's my middle name.
- Yeah.
You're older. She knows
she's older than me.
[April] And I'm older
than him.
[Billy] I met her
when I was 17.
I seduced you.
Honestly,
Joey's handling things
at the table
way better than I would be
because I would have
been calling his ass out.
I would have told him
to leave the table
and take his leather coat
with him.
My first impression is
he's dripping
- in toxic masculinity...
- There we go.
[Kelle] ...and he clearly
needs a lot of attention,
which is pretty embarrassing
at his age.
Yeah, that's true.
Sure you don't want
to bite of steak?
[Billy speaking]
Stop!
See what I mean?
That's why I have
three children with this man.
Twins.
That's two sperm.
Two eggs, my friend.
I mean, clearly,
we see the reason
why Billy is her ex,
but on the other hand,
how can he keep master
manipulating her
still after all these years?
The behavior
obviously is the same.
I don't know
why she would accept
his bad energy back when,
you know,
preaching good energy.
Yeah. Yeah, exactly.
Ooh.
What are you eating?
Oh, oh, I'm eating the steak.
[April]
We're both having steak.
I think that Billy
is just kind of focusing
on me,
it seems like,
and he doesn't even notice
Joey there,
to be quite honest.
But you know,
Billy's Billy and he's just
gonna do what he's gonna do.
I kind of feel bad for Joey
because, you know, we were
on a date and Billy just came
and changed the whole story.
I want to ask you
some questions, though.
- [Ryan] Okay.
- [Pola] Oh, yeah.
- All right.
- I'm an open book.
[Emma] Do you...
do you have children?
- [Ryan] No.
- Do you want children?
Um, I mean, I'm...
one day I'd be open to it.
Yeah, because my mom
doesn't want
any more children.
I mean, it's not necessarily
a deal breaker for me.
[Pola] Really it's not.
Not, it's not.
Like, I just want to be
extremely happy and...
I agree with you 100%.
And I don't know
about the age.
Um-hmm.
She has a very young, genuine,
given outgoing spirit
and like, I'm extremely
attracted to that.
Nice.
[Pola] Ryan tells me
every single day
that he loves Jose
and that he sees himself
with my family.
But I just need to get Jose
and Emma's approval.
For me family is and
will always be the most
important part of my life.
I really need to know
how you feel about
me being with Ryan?
Like you always told us,
like my brother and myself,
that right now, like,
the most important people
are both of us.
Like my brother and myself.
But right now,
we're all really grown up.
And I think your job is done,
completely done.
And you did a terrific job.
You did a very good job.
I think it's time
to focus on yourself.
[Pola] Thank you.
And I think like
whichever guy you choose,
we're gonna be supportive.
We're gonna be proud.
And honestly, you need to...
you need to start living.
[Pola] I agree.
Thank you.
[Ryan] Emma's cosign
and approval is extremely
important to me at this point.
So based on how highly Pola
speaks of Emma,
I have her blessing.
It's 100% necessary.
What's going on? Like...
- [Stefany] Oh, my God.
- I want to know.
I'm excited. I want to know.
What's going on?
I'm opening up to potentially
like, you know,
the fact that he's 23.
I mean, he's made me
felt so special.
But you've never
dated someone...
- [Stefany] Older.
- ...older before?
- Never, right?
- Not to this extent.
[Peace] Okay.
You too, right?
[Stefany] Yeah, no.
I've never...
- Because we've talked and...
- [Stefany] Yeah, I've... Yeah.
No, she was never,
like, you're, like, no.
- [Stefany] Not younger guys.
- That's too young.
So I'm like, just be open.
You never know.
[Stefany] I mean,
he doesn't, you know,
I mean, you don't act 23.
And Stefany,
you see this guy as the one
or just get into the one
or what? What is it?
That was a little bit
of an awkward question.
You know, it was probably
even awkward for Gabriel.
I've definitely not had
a chance to talk to Gabriel
about any of this.
I'm not even sure if Gabriel,
you know, wants to be married.
- We'll see.
- We'll see?
What God's plan is.
Are you hesitant
or do you think...
No. I think because
we've taken it so slow...
[Peace] Okay.
...and we've established
this amazing connection.
[Gabriel]
What scares me is that, like,
sometimes when you
establish something
so strong with someone,
if you make it, it's just
such a romantic level.
It could totally be ruined
in like six months.
[Stefany] This is definitely
reality check.
You know, love's a risk
and I'm willing
to put it all out there.
But why would I
put myself all in
if, you know,
he's not willing to do so?
It makes me question
if this is even
gonna go anywhere.
Love takes time.
I mean, you don't
have to rush,
but at the same time,
you still have to know
what you want.
They've heard
so much about you.
Umm.
I feel like I know you.
Yeah.
But I don't know
anything about you.
[Jose] I know.
I know you don't.
I have a tough question
for you.
For who? For me?
- [McKenna] Both of you.
- Okay.
- Oh.
- Drum roll.
How far has your intimacy
gone?
[Kelle] Why are you
looking at me?
You looked at me.
Every time that subject comes
up, you just, like, clam up.
I'm just looking at you
and, you.
Oh, just come out...
You're looking at both of us.
I'm looking we got stuck
in together.
What are you,
getting nervous?
I'm not.
There's nothing to be
nervous about.
Hmm.
I mean,
I think it's the same thing
as we've been doing.
We're taking it slow.
McKenna is definitely someone
with a very strong personality,
and it's someone
that I in a way,
I'm gonna have a challenge
in to earning her acceptance.
So how do you feel
about her having six kids?
I... it's amazing.
- [McKenna] Yeah.
- Yeah.
Good answer.
Do you want kids?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I love the fact
that McKenna is grilling Jose
because she's asking him
all the questions
I actually wanted to know.
McKenna can read anybody.
So if Jose is, like,
playing a game,
she's definitely gonna
sniff it out.
I still want
to get to know you
because she's extremely
special to me.
The most amazing soul ever.
[Jose] For sure.
And, you know,
I'm really protective,
but I'm happy to be here.
For sure.
Yeah, I'm happy you're here.
I'm happy to meet you.
Yeah, thank you.
Thank you.
So after having
this conversation with Jose,
I definitely want
to put him through
a little bit of a test.
I do have some reservations,
but we'll see.
You're very cute.
I'm blushing.
Don't blush.
So...
[Emma speaking]
Emma showing up
definitely changes the game.
Starting to wonder,
if April
is the right one for me.
[Jose] How are you
feeling, buddy?
I'm still thinking about
what happened
in the restaurant, bro.
I was furious.
Yeah.
- In the future,
that must not happen.
- Yeah.
Billy, he was trying to,
like, set a boundary that,
like, wasn't really...
- He was trying to show off...
- [Joey] Yeah.
...and get attention,
and you were making her happy.
- And he is not.
- I know.
So you should be very proud
of who you are
and take that wherever you go.
Yeah. And I will.
[McKenna] Hello, darlings.
Hello, darling.
- How are you?
- McKenna, how are you doing?
- Good. But I do want
to steal you.
- You want to steal me?
- Yeah.
Okay.
I definitely want to take time
in to talk to Jose
because I don't know him.
So there is some digging
I need to do for sure.
Thank you.
[Jose] You're welcome, McKenna.
- [McKenna] Ooh.
- [Jose] Be careful.
- [McKenna] Will I
break this?
- No, no, it's been delicate.
It's been delicate for...
I don't know.
I work out pretty hard.
[Jose] That's cool.
So with my mom,
when was the moment
where you wanted
to choose her like?
So ever since the doors
open, we saw everybody.
- I mean,
she stood out for sure.
- Um-hmm.
I mean, from the look
in my eyes.
Hmm.
Do you want to, like,
settle down?
- Eventually, yeah.
- Eventually?
For sure.
Because McKenna
is so similar to Kelle,
they both have
a very strong personality.
So I was not surprised
when McKenna started
shooting all these questions.
For me personally,
it's easy to connect
with people,
but the intensity
of the connection...
[Jose] A 100%, yeah.
...you know, the throw me
against the
wall connections...
Yes.
Make out with me anywhere connection.
[Jose] For sure.
You know, do you have that
with my mom?
Your mom has become
someone very special for me.
Like, really.
But I tell her that
I like things...
take things slow.
- Um-hmm.
- Is that you?
A little bit. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
That's my...
I don't like to rush.
[McKenna] Um-hmm.
But I know my mom,
and she needs more touch.
She's more physicality.
You can respect a woman,
you still spank her.
Like, like, guys do it
all the time.
Push her against the wall
and tell her how it is.
Yeah.
But Jose's a cutie.
He's a little more reserved
than what I'm used to,
um, same with my mom, too.
So, okay, I have
one more hard question.
Yeah, go ahead.
It's just... if I asked you
to go on a date with me,
would you?
Um...
Okay.
- No.
- No?
No. I do respect
for your mom. No.
That's a good answer.
Well, you never know, because
there's been situations...
- Really?
- There has been situation,
one situation.
- Really? Like that.
- Yeah.
I think that's disrespectful.
- For both of you.
I agree.
With some of
McKenna's questions,
I get the impression
that she believes that
Kelle and I are not aligned
in a lot of different aspects
of our lives,
which makes me question
as well,
if it's a match for me or not.
- Well, let's go back inside.
- Let's go.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, McKenna.
- [McKenna] You're so sweet.
- Thank you.
[Joey] It's been a long day,
and I'm a little bummed
about how today turned out.
And after being ignored
by Miss April
and her ex-husband
and I still haven't been able
to talk to April yet.
I feel like I'm kind of
just like left out
in the open alone.
So I really need
to get some clarity
to see if April takes me
as seriously
as I'm taking her.
What are you doing?
Just chilling out.
Yeah. Can I talk to you
for a second?
- [Joey] Yeah, of course.
- Yeah?
- [Joey] Of course.
- Are you busy or something?
No, no.
I'm really excited
to talk to Emma.
It definitely feels
good to get a little bit
of attention today
by someone that might
actually want to talk to me.
I ain't gonna lie.
So you're very cute.
Thank you. Thank you.
- You're.
- You're too.
I'm very picky with people,
like, the people that
I... that I like.
I'm blushing.
Don't blush.
You're like a little red.
[Joey] When a woman
starts hitting on me,
I try to play it cool.
Maybe I like, blush a little
bit, but, like, I know I got
the suave and the swag.
I keep it pretty cool.
I try to keep
a straight face.
What did you think about me?
Oh, the second I saw you,
I was like,
that is
a spitting image of Pola.
Because you don't know,
but Pola...
But that's a good thing.
Yeah, oh, great thing.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
But, yeah,
I love your mother.
She's very beautiful.
Oh, really?
And when I saw you today,
I was like, "Oh, my God.
- That is Pola's daughter,
for sure."
- Yeah.
You are like, Oh, my God,
you're such a good person.
I could just tell just by
looking in someone's eyes.
You could really tell
if they're being genuine
or not.
Yeah.
So...
I mean, since day one,
it's been, you know, like
I said, our chemistry
is really met,
but it's hard to say
whether she's gonna be
my girlfriend or not.
I'm a little hurt about
what happened earlier today
with April,
and I'm starting to wonder
if April
is the right one for me.
So you'll be down to know me?
Honestly, I'm kind of torn.
As much as I love
talking to April,
I like talking to Emma, too.
Oh, I'd be down
and get to know you
way better.
[Emma] Okay. Awesome.
What did I just get
myself into?
Holy [bleep]
[woman] Okay.
I don't know this could get
out of control really quickly.
[woman] Oh.
[indistinct]
[Pola] I was watching,
but I was not watching.
For me, it's not fun.
When Billy came in,
I was so excited to meet him.
And when he took you away,
I kind of felt, like,
disrespected in a way.
If there's a chance
you guys will talk.
Excuse my language,
but I could give [bleep]
get to know him.
You will each write a letter
to your partner
stating your intentions
and if you would like
this relationship
to continue outside the villa.
[Kelle]
I'm really emotional writing
this letter to Jose right now
because for the first time
I feel like I really have
connected with somebody
who gets me
and actually has my back.
And, um, I really just
don't want to say goodbye.
I sincerely have nothing but
good to say about you, Joey.
Our journey's
coming to an end,
it's time for me to...
to tell him how I feel.
And I just hope
we're both on the same page.
I can't even begin to express
the emotions
that are currently running
through my head.
I want to be sincere.
I want to be clear,
but I'm not really clear
because I don't know
if there's gonna be
a future or not.
[Gabriel]
This is scary because
we are such good friends
that if we turn it romantic,
it could ruin
our lifelong friendship.
[Stefany] So this is it.
I want to get married again.
You know, I'm hoping
that he could be ready
for some commitment here.
Do you think there's a chance
for us to be a couple
when we get back to L.A.?