I've been told,
I'm a very good kisser.
[laughs]
Oh, my God.
Billy's definitely one
of my favorites.
Billy and I had
a good time today.
He was amazing.
He said, he has a big [bleep].
[Stefany] Kelle is a little
wild for him.
- No.
- No?
- Not at all.
- Okay.
Just make sure I'm not around.
[Kelle laughs]
I love your eyes.
Thank you.
Stefany caught my eye
because she just seems
so sweet,
and I think she's
super pretty.
I'm excited.
We are the best.
I'm gonna ask Stefany
to come dancing
with me tonight.
[all cheering]
[Gabriel] I was
kind of bummed.
I don't really have my eye
on anyone else.
You went on a date
with Harrison.
He's a smooth guy, huh?
[Ryan] Gabriel's just doing
a little too much for me.
Gabriel likes attention.
Have you been to
Bulgaria before?
It's just been fun.
Like, more friends.
[Stefany] I do like Gabriel
a lot.
but I'm a little confused
at this point.
I'm gonna be down
for you but you gotta
make time.
Cheers to more dates.
I think that she's interested
in me...
a hundred percent.
[Shannan] So, there's been
some developments
in the villa.
I'm not the one to gossip
but it looks like
Billy and Kelle are taking
things to the next level.
And how cute
is it that April J and Joey,
the oldest person
and the youngest person
in the house,
have this love connection
going on.
I have no idea what's going
on with April W and Ricky.
They are always MIA.
And I know that Ryan
has his eyes set on Stefany,
however, you know, Stefany
and Gabriel
are definitely spending more
time together,
and so she needs to woman up
and be clear about what
it is that she wants,
and who she wants it with.
[Ryan] How you feeling?
I'm always feeling great.
Aw!
I just went on a date
with Ryan yesterday.
I had a great time.
I felt a connection with him,
so, I'm definitely open
to getting to know each other
a little better.
- [Ryan] You taking my ...
- I know.
I'm tired.
[Ryan] Um, me too.
You're so, like, ready to go
to like a Hollywood bar
or something.
- [Ryan] You said,
a Hollywood bar?
- [Stefany] Yeah.
Me and Stef, at this point,
are kind of building on what
we've been building on.
I'm doing my thing.
I think that we developed
a very strong connection.
It's not a forged chemistry.
I think it's been
pretty genuine.
- Oh, no.
- I want to be like you when
I grow up.
You know what I'm saying?
Ryan keeps trying to, like,
hit on Stefany and stuff.
I'm not one to judge
but Stefany's just--
she likes to play nice,
you know, sometimes.
So, I feel like that could
definitely be read as like,
"Oh! She might like you,"
you know.
This is fun.
He tries so hard to, like,
try and make his moves
and stuff, you know.
So then, I pull up,
I'm like, "Stefany."
- [Gabriel] Come on.
- That's so true, like, when--
[Gabriel] Lets dance.
[Stefany cheering]
I just think it's funny.
Okay.
I just think it's kind of lame
if you see me vibing
with somebody,
if you see me in the middle
of a conversation,
for you to, like, come and try
to, like, disrupt that vibe.
You know, you're telling me,
this guy's just a friend,
you know, you would never
consider really dating him,
like, I'm confused
at this point.
How am I your favorite?
And how are you acting
like that?
'Cause at the end of the day
you can't play with him.
And I can't blame
him if you are.
You gotta draw
a line somewhere.
[both speaking in Spanish]
- Exactly.
- [Jose] Salud.
So far, who are the ladies
that you're interested
in getting to know better?
So...
Soyoung, I mean, you can
sense her energy, right?
[Ryan] Yeah.
Incredible energy.
- [Ryan] Unexpected energy.
- For sure.
'Cause she's not super vocal,
but, like, when you hop
in the zone,
- she's like, yeah.
- For sure.
[Jose] Your mom is one
of the ladies that I think
- that she is the most
interesting and elegant.
- [Ryan] Got you.
[Ryan] I think Jose has
a relevant shot with my mom.
He seems very genuine
and daring.
So, that's definitely
my mom's style.
Other than that,
not gonna lie,
Jose has a great accent.
[laughs]
- You?
- [Ryan] Um...
I'm going to be honest,
- my date with Stefany
was amazing.
- [Jose] Yeah?
[Ryan laughs]
[Stefany]
- So far, what I've gotten
from her has been really cool.
- [Jose] Okay.
But it's just so far
I'm feeling between
because of the dynamic
that Gabriel has...
- [Jose] For sure.
- ...with her.
[Ryan] My girl, I can barely
get her out of the corner.
Yeah. Literally,
my conversation was,
"Look, this is how I feel
about you,
and I'm interested in building
on that.
You gotta tell that dude,
if that's not your intent
with him,
then don't give
him a different narrative."
I see myself being
in a potential match
with Stefany
but the elephant in the room
is Gabriel.
All I'm looking for,
at this point, is clarity
on this situation.
The worst thing you can do
to somebody is not be honest,
- I'm telling you that now.
- [Jose] For sure.
[Ryan] Nobody wants to build
relationships like that.
- You need to know that when
you're with someone,
- [Ryan] Come on.
you can trust.
[Ryan] That's what we need.
- Salud with that.
[laughs]
You pack your suitcase
just for your hats?
[Shannan speaking]
You look great in hats.
Everyone! Daters...
It's time for you to decide
whether or not you have
chemistry with the other
people in the villa.
If you are already vibing
with someone then carry on.
But if you're unsure
whether you have a connection,
then listen up.
For the next hour,
everyone in the house
should take five minutes
getting to know anyone
they're unsure about.
This has nothing to do
with looks.
You're trying to determine
whether you have chemistry
with that person.
You will interact with someone
you haven't before
to rate them
on chemistry scale.
We have to rate each person
from one to ten. And...
so, bring your 'A' game.
[all cheering]
[Ryan] I like it.
I like speed dating.
it is kind of old school.
It's kind of a classic
feel but...
I like stuff like that.
- [laughs]
- [laughs] So...
[Soyoung] I never done
a speed dating, ever.
I still don't have any
connection to anybody.
So, I'm definitely ready
for meeting all men.
Hopefully, Jose comes.
[laughs]
[Charlene] You're this so
L.A. vibe,
are you really looking
for love? Or, I mean,
do you want--
Honestly, I'm such a lover,
I even put lover boy
on my thing.
Yeah.
[chuckles]
But, uh, I'm very romantic
and everything.
What about in the bedroom?
- Uh...
- Be honest. That's fine.
I'm just curious.
Are you good in bed?
What's, like, your
signature move?
Do you have one?
What gets you going?
Is it the boobs?
I mean, could that be?
Or are you a butt man?
Like, what's going to seal
the deal for you that, like,
we got-- it's there?
I, kind of, am the type
of person where I just
don't jump into something,
- if it makes sense.
- Right.
I view it very, like,
spiritual, like,
that's my temple,
that's someone temple,
it really has to be super
important and like, special.
Oh.
[Gabriel] Charlene kept
jumping in and...
straight up to the point.
She's like, "So, how do
you like it in bed?"
Like, tell me about your...
your sex life.
Like, it was just so much.
And for me to talk about
to a random stranger, like,
to just be vulnerable
and open up like that
was uncomfortable.
- I didn't even know
that happened.
- Yeah.
You know, she was talking
about, like...
- She's pretty straightforward.
- Straightforward.
[Gabriel] Which isn't bad
but definitely not...
- Just... Yeah.
- ...my cup of tea, I think.
[Charlene] I'm a really
good kisser.
I had a lot of practice
in high school
that I was a above the waist
kind of gal. I still am.
I was called
"The queen of blue balls."
Damn.
Communication is important.
I know what my needs are
and I know they needed
to be met, like yesterday.
I've been ready to go out into
the deep end.
Like, does anybody know
how to swim here or what?
What are some of, like,
your hobbies?
Oh, boy.
Fun.
[Jimmy] All right.
Well, I picked you.
I definitely wanted to get
to know you more.
- [Stefany] That's sweet.
- I'm...
[stammers]
- [laughs]
- I'm interested...
Why me, though?
You have great skin.
You have good taste.
- I love the anklet.
- [laughs]
Yeah. I love toe rings,
anklets, feet.
Soft skin, nice legs,
nice hands.
I'm definitely
feeling Stefany.
She's cool. She's like,
you know, she doesn't
feel that...
you know, older than
me, really.
- I don't know.
- You think she's my type?
Well, she's a cool person
but she's not your type.
She might have a wide,
but she don't have out.
- Yeah. You know I like
the out. Like...
- [laughs]
[Jose] Buenas noches. Hellos.
- Jose!
- [Jose] Very happy
to be here with you.
- [Soyoung] Oh! You are.
Thank you.
- I am.
- [Soyoung] I'm very
happy, too.
- You're cold?
- No.
- [Jose] No?
Now, I'm getting hot.
- Hot, okay. Okay. Okay.
- [laughs]
Jose, he's got, like,
height and the eyes
and, you know, the F's
and all the style
that I've been looking for.
[inhales deeply]
I'm like, mmm-mmm.
Ever since I got here,
all, they're asking me,
"Oh! Who do you think
that you could date?"
I chose you.
Well, I'm glad that
this happened.
- [Soyoung] Yeah.
- So, we-- we both know now
and we're both in agreement.
- [Soyoung] Mmm-hmm.
- For sure.
- [Jose] Definitely.
- Yeah. That's awesome.
There's something about
you that just makes you glow.
I considering your eyes
and I considering the way
that you... that you speak,
I would love to go on a date
or something.
- Mmm. Okay.
- [Jose] Like, to get to know
each other
with more than four minutes.
Maybe a dinner or something.
I think there's a chance,
like, to get that connection,
you know.
Okay. Yes.
[inhales deeply]
Jose just asked me to date.
I was shocked that he's been
thinking about me.
I thought I had loved Jose
but now I love him more
than ever.
[laughs]
Sounds good. I love it.
[Shannan] So, what's the first
thing that, like, you might
be attracted to?
Like, eyes or a smile.
- Being honest...
- Mmm-hmm
Your feet.
- You... you got a foot fetish?
- Yeah.
- Oh, Lord.
[laughs]
- [Ricky] So, like, if...
[Shannan] Ricky is hilarious.
I feel like I'm at home
with Ricky
because he is from Detroit,
I grew up in Detroit.
But, yeah, I need a little
bit more energy.
- You're like a undercover
freak or somethin'.
- Yes. I'm like that.
[Shannan laughs]
I'mma always keep
my feet tight.
My game is just
with me and me.
Like, if I got to go outside
myself and meet you,
like, I don't need
to have you.
You're very quiet.
My personality is talk to me,
I'll talk back.
Like, I'm not gonna be
like, hi.
So, I'm curious, who do
you have your eye on?
- I don't want to say
any names.
- [Kelle] Why?
[Kelle] Why not?
If you want something,
you say it and you go for it.
I don't want to say
what I want.
Trying to get to know Ricky
on this speed date
but literally he's not saying
anything, asking no questions.
The fact that he doesn't speak
unless spoken to,
is like super weird to me.
It is the first time
that we actually had time
to really...
I know.
So, what kind of things
do you like?
- Music, concerts or--
- [Ricky] I like-- I'm not--
I'm not really a music person.
Oh, really?
Like, I'm like an onion, like,
you gotta peel me back.
Yeah.
Well, let me get real
with you.
Like, physical attraction.
How important is that
big booty? You know, like...
- Uh, you know what?
- [chuckles]
The results of the chemistry
tests are in.
There's one mother and son
- that scored the lowest.
- Oh.
- And they will be going home.
- [gasps]
- [woman 1] No.
- [woman 2] What? No.
[Charlene] So, was I on
your list?
- You were definitely
on my list.
- Oh, okay.
Um, I was like, I would like
to know.
- [Charlene] Well, that's nice.
- I was very curious.
I am still into Stefany,
but I'm open to dating
other ladies in the house.
You never know.
My match could be right under
my nose and I might not even
know her yet.
What are some things that are
important to you,
first of all?
Well, let me get real
with you.
Like, physical attraction.
How important is that big
booty, though?
You know, like...
- Uh, you know what?
- [Charlene] Come on.
[chuckles]
'Cause that's what I'll think.
I'll be like...
- I like big booty, okay.
- [Charlene] Nah!
- [Charlene] I mean, come on.
- I'm an ass man.
- [laughs]
- Okay. Honestly,
I'm a ass man.
- Like--
- A shocker. Oh, my God.
I'm so shocked.
[both laughing]
I just think a lot of men
that are ass men
that they're ass driven.
It's like, ass first.
- [laughs]
- [Charlene] Like, is that's
your focus?
Charlene is a whole body
aggressive woman.
So, I'm not surprised when
she's telling me what
she's telling me,
but it might be a little
too pushy for me.
I'll ask you some more
questions later.
Thank you.
She is saying what she wants
and she's not apologetic
about it.
So, hey, to each it's own,
it's gonna work,
for some people it might
not though, for others.
- [Billy] Hi.
- [April W] Oh!
My first person.
- Hey, Billy. How are you?
- Good.
- All right. So. I'm gonna ask
you some questions.
- [Billy] Okay.
- Um...
- [April W] Are
you spontaneous?
I would say
I'm very spontaneous.
Are you aggressive?
Mmm-mmm.
If you want to kiss
will you take it?
I'm sometimes the type
of person that will, like,
ask like...
do you want to kiss?
In a sense...
April Watson needs to work
on her interviewing skills.
[laughs]
Will you pull a jimmy?
Sorry.
What was Jimmy's dirty secret?
I got pink eye from
[bleep] ass.
[all cheering and laughing]
I knew it!
It's a normal thing.
- Oh! [bleep]
- [laughs]
- I'm not [bleep] completely.
Okay.
- How about you? Did you ever
pull a jimmy?
- [April W] Hey! Hey!
I won't pull a jimmy.
That doesn't mean
I don't like the jimmy.
- Oh! For sure.
- [both laughing]
[April W laughs]
Oh, God!
Uh, it was a little
bit intimidating.
Well, it was nice chatting.
- Nice chatting with you, too.
- [Billy] Cool.
- I appreciate it.
- [Billy] Take it easy.
I have such
a strong personality,
I would totally dominate
somebody like Billy.
And I wouldn't want to do that
because he's such a sweet guy.
- How are you doing?
- Hey, Joey.
So, my question
to you is, Joey,
what makes you experienced
enough for an older woman?
You need to sell me on that.
Are you talking about sexually
- Yeah.
- or just everything?
- Sexually.
- Sexually!
Okay. Well, I haven't had, uh,
like, as much sexual
experience as you.
Have you ever been
with a older woman?
I have not been
with a older woman sexually.
Okay.
Would you ever pull a jimmy?
- A jimmy?
- [laughs]
That's just out
of my comfort zone.
What is up with no one wants
to pull a jimmy!
I will do most of the things
that you want me to do.
- Except [bleep] ass.
- Yeah.
[April W] That's good to know.
[Joey] It's a little awkward.
Would I ever do the jimmy
to her?
I didn't know she was coming
on like with you.
- She did it to everyone.
- What?
[Jose] It's a pleasure getting
time to connect
- Right.
- and to learn a little more
about you.
- So--
- So, if you saw me at a bar,
would you asked me, like,
my age?
I would be so interested
to learn so many things
about you before your age.
When you meet somebody,
what's the first thing
- that catches you eye?
- Um...
The smile.
- [Jose] Yeah?
- Definitely. Yeah.
You have a really
amazing smile.
- Thank you. Thank you.
You do, too, as well.
- Yeah.
Jose and I are definitely
hitting it off.
But I think at this time
I'm content where, you know,
things are with Ryan
and Gabriel.
So, I don't want to add more
to my plate.
Only God knows where,
you know, he's going
to lead me.
And hopefully, soon I will
find out.
- Gracias, senorita.
- Oh, my gosh.
This is awesome stuff.
[Jose] It is. It is indeed.
- [Joey] Hello, Pola.
- [speaking in Spanish]
- Yeah. How you doing?
- [Pola] Very good. And you?
- I'm doing great.
- [Pola] So...
What are you looking for here?
I'm looking
for a great person.
You want, like, older woman?
Yeah. I flirt with them.
You know, I love dancing
with them.
- How old?
- I would say 50 to 60.
- Oh, my God. Okay.
- [Joey] I'm not-- Yeah.
I'm not--
I'm not lying. Especially,
you probably--
You got you that...
you got you that tight body.
You got that slim fit, so...
- Of course, I'd like to see
that body in the sheets.
- [laughs]
Like, how would I not?
Pola is very attractive.
Her little accent, yeah,
that's kind of cool, too.
I like that.
Maybe I got it from my mom
because she loves herself
a Brazilian accent.
- What I would like to see
in a older woman...
- Uh-huh.
- is her actually not see
me as a child...
- [Pola] Okay.
and see me as an adult.
And what are you going
to show us here?
I-- I'm really going
to show...
how I really am.
I know. But really, what are
you going to show?
My speed date with Joey,
it was a disaster.
[speaking in Spanish]
- Take care.
- [laughs]
- You, too.
Wait. Who just took
the Tabasco that I just
brought to the table?
I mean, I want it but I was
just wondering.
- [phone rings and vibrates]
- I got a text!
[all cheering]
Attention, daters.
The results of the chemistry
tests are in.
Some of you are rated
very high,
while others didn't pair
as well.
[all exclaiming]
That's to be expected.
The mother and son who ranked
the highest are...
- drum roll.
- [all tapping table]
Pola and Jose!
[all cheering]
I love everybody.
[Pola] Thank you.
It's great to see that people
are as receptive towards us
- as we're towards them.
- Yeah. I wasn't... I wasn't
expecting this to happen
but I really feel comfortable
because we like everyone.
And it's good to know
that they like us as well.
- Yeah. For sure.
- So, I'm really happy.
Yay!
[laughs]
Excuse me. I would
like to know who
the lowest is, please.
[phone rings and vibrates]
You guys.
I have a text now.
[all cheering]
And now for the bad news.
- [woman 1] Oh.
- [man 1] Oh.
There is one mother and son
that scored the lowest.
- Oh.
- And they will be going home.
- [woman 2 gasps]
- [woman 3] No.
- [woman 4] What the...
- [woman 5] No.
- [woman 4] What?
- [man 2] Are you serious?
I'm dead serious.
I didn't think anybody
was going home.
Oh, God. I'm like,
I'm about to cry.
- [woman 6] Wait.
Are you [bleep]
- [woman 7] Oh!
There is one mother and son
that scored the lowest.
- Oh.
- And they will be going home.
- [woman 2 gasps]
- [woman 3] No.
- [woman 4] What the...
- [woman 5] No.
- [woman 4] What?
- [man 2] Are you serious?
I'm dead serious.
Somebody's going home.
Like, I didn't even know
that was ever even an option.
So, I'm-- I'm...
I'm just... I'm just shocked.
Oh, God. I'm like,
I'm about to cry.
- [woman 6] Wait.
Are you [bleep]
- [woman 7] Oh!
[Shannan] April and Ricky...
unfortunately the connection
is not quite there
and it's time for you to leave
the villa.
- Oh, my God.
- Wow!
I didn't think that anybody
was leaving.
This is like... Whoo!
- [man 2] I don't think--
- It's not a joke.
Please say your goodbyes.
- [woman 5] What? No.
- [woman 6] Wait. What?
[man 3] No way.
- [man 4] What?
- No.
So, it's not a connection.
It's just shocking.
- No.
- Aw!
[Billy] Ricky and April
are going home.
They didn't really make
an effort to really like...
- Connect.
- ...connect with anyone else
other than themselves.
[Soyoung] April is wonderful
but I don't really know her.
Or she's now really
in a group.
- And he's not really
there, either.
- Yeah.
- So...
- He didn't want to be there.
They didn't want to be there.
[Ricky] All right. I'm out
of here.
I'm going to my room.
I have no kitty party.
[Gabriel] April and Ricky
going home
kind of shocked everyone.
People are kind of scared now,
I think.
So, they're all going to try
and start pumping up
their game.
Everything has changed now.
How do you feel about
the change?
I'm totally fine with it.
The way that I operate is,
if you'd want to be somewhere
don't be there.
- Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
- If that's what you're
gonna do
that's what people
are gonna feel.
- [Charlene] Right.
- And then they won't connect
with you,
and then it's like,
that's what's gonna happen.
[April W speaking]
[April W] I'm not mad
and I'm not sad.
I'm the same feeling that I am
when I found that we was
dating y'all, shocked.
I think I got a low score
because I came off
very reserved,
so, it was kind of hard
to have, like,
a sexual connection
with really anybody.
It was... just weird,
if I had to be honest.
So, I get it.
Jose...
[bleep] This... this is real.
I mean, that's gonna feel bad,
if I'm in their shoes.
I mean, it is shocking
because I didn't know
they were gonna go home.
[April W] Oh, Soyoung.
[laughs]
Don't feel bad, Soyoung.
- [Jose] Love you, man.
- [Ricky] Love you, too, man.
[Pola] Senor, thank you
for everything.
It was a real pleasure.
Yeah. Thank you.
[Jose] Seeing what happened
with April and Ricky,
I realized that chemistry
and finding
that romantic person
in this house
is super important.
- See you, guys!
- [all cheering and applauding]
[Ricky] I'm reserved.
Like, I don't know
how to just open up.
I have to observe the scene
and then I'll open up.
So, it was...
it was actually like,
it was a eye-opener for me.
[April W] Ricky and I came
on this retreat looking
for a partner.
Never thought that would be
so hard to find.
I'm speechless.
- [man 2] Bye, Detroit.
- [man 3] Bye.
Damn! This is crazy.
[Jose] That's a cool spot.
- That is very nice.
- [Jose laughs]
[both sigh]
- This is nice.
- [Jose laughs]
It is indeed.
- This is good. This is good.
- For sure.
I like Soyoung a lot
but Shannan is a very
special woman.
After seeing Ricky and April
leave for not finding
a connection,
I now realize that the main
purpose of this
whole experience
is to look for those
deep connections
and embrace them
and elevate them.
Have you dated women
that are older?
Yeah. She was like...
two or three years
older than me.
- [Shannan] Okay.
- Yeah.
How do you feel when you see
the exterior of me,
being an older woman?
- I mean, I see your elegance.
- All right.
I'll take that.
[Shannan] Jose is hard
to figure out.
I feel like he may give
everyone that kind
of attention.
So, you don't know
if you're special.
- Have you dated younger...
- [Shannan] Mmm-hmm.
I have.
You know, I think age ain't
nothing but a number.
I always say that, actually.
It's very important to break
with all those misconceptions
about how--
[Shannan] This is true.
- We're supposed to feel or see
ourselves in a certain age.
- [Shannan] Right.
I think that's probably
the most attractive about you
- is the fact that...
- Thank you. Thank you.
...you know, that you have
that insight, you know,
that intellect.
- Appreciate it. Thank you.
- [laughs]
- [Jose] Yeah. I love it.
- Are you blushing?
- Am I?
- I don't know.
- You are blushing.
[Jose] The more I know
and learn from Shannan,
the more I like her.
- And--
- I love her. I love her.
She's very nice. She's...
She's very smart and also
she's quite.
- Yes.
- She doesn't scream.
- A very soft voice. Yeah.
- Soft. Yeah.
And you know what I like
about her?
How she talks to her son.
- They have a very nice
relationship between them.
- Yeah.
- What are you looking for?
- [Shannan] Um...
In life-- Like, in general.
I do just have just one life.
And I want to make the most
of it.
And there's a saying
in Spanish.
[speaking in Spanish]
[Shannan] Dude, that
sounds sexy.
What does that mean?
[laughs]
That-- it's basically that
nobody takes your experience
from you.
Mmm. That's hot.
I like Jose.
So, I am trying to figure out
what exactly is going to get
him to that next level.
I have been married twice.
And when it comes to dating
in between marriages,
I will say that my attention
span has been a little short.
But I feel like I have
a connection with Jose.
He has my attention.
Wait.
- [sighs]
I got it.
- Don't make us fall.
I'm trying to.
[sighs]
This is good.
Whoo-wee!
- [Gabriel] You get comfy.
Lay down.
- [Stefany] You took my--
What's your favorite part
of this trip so far?
- Just meeting--
- Besides me.
Oh, besides you.
[laughs]
Just meeting everyone.
I think...
- It's fun, huh?
- It's been fun. Yes.
[Gabriel] Are you comfy?
Or are you falling?
Put your legs.
I'm perfect.
I'm perfect, too.
So, we're good.
We're perfect.
[laughs]
- [Gabriel] So funny.
- [Stefany] Oh, my goodness.
- Ryan!
- [Ryan] What's up?
Do you play any, like,
instruments and [bleep]?
I play some violin
and play some piano by ear.
Could we get a little
grand piano?
[laughs] That's good.
You want to stay here, too?
Stefany, offer him a spot,
I'm out.
[both laughing]
[Stefany] Did you hear him?
This is like a weird case
of, like, actions and words
not matching.
So, I'm confused
at this point.
Like, how am I your favorite?
And if you're telling somebody
that they're strictly,
clearly just a friend,
and they know their position,
then why is he moving the way
he's moving?
You know.
We're two perfect people.
[laughs]
- We're two gorgeous, gorgeous,
gorgeous girls.
- Yeah.
[laughs]
Yes. Yes.
- [Gabriel] We're just friends.
- We're friends.
[both laughing]
It's very annoying
where Gabriel is.
Too overbearing.
I don't wanna get him upset.
I don't want to get you upset.
You gotta draw that line
or nothing else will
really develop.
[Stefany] Billy!
[Kelle] Billy and I are
turning up the heat.
Do you not knock?
[Stefany] Oh, yeah.
Kelle, you got to go.
We should get in the hot tub.
Do you want to get into
Pola's and Jose's?
The one in their room is...
it doesn't turn on. Remember?
Let's try.
The speed dating thing
was kind of buzz for me.
I didn't have any new matches
but I am here to find love.
So, since Billy and I had
a little connection
on our date on the beach,
I think we need to turn up
the heat.
I'm jealous of your feet.
- Oh!
- They're very arched.
Look how flat my feet are.
It's flat, flat.
Damn! Look at that.
That's what I'm saying
you got.
You come over,
you can see your toes.
- I just spread my toes.
- [Ryan] Oh, look at all
your moves.
You're a little duck!
[Stefany speaking]
[Ryan]
Did he kick you out?
- He didn't text you?
- No one's kicking me out
of my room.
[Ryan] I mean, you have like
three rooms in one room.
- That's true.
- [Ryan] I think you're good.
So, Gabriel says he was going
to take me out on a date.
That was--
Of course, he does.
It's very annoying where
Gabriel is.
You know, too overbearing
when it comes to Gabriel.
I feel like he never leaves.
Seriously. He just
is always there.
The degree of separation
with Stefany is none.
So, I have to create
some separation
just to see if it's a fit
or not a fit, you know.
I think what bothers
me is the lack
of respecting boundaries.
Like, if I'm sitting
with you at the pool
right now,
like, he'll, like, come back
and come over and be, like,
-"Hey, Stef."
- Oh.
Like, bro, like stop.
- You know what
I'm saying. Like...
- I get it.
[April J] Gabriel had been
hanging out with Stefany
the whole time.
And Ryan was kind of looking
out for himself going,
you know,
"Who am I going to be with?"
And he started competing
with my kid.
And Ryan's cool.
But, you know, if somebody's
going to start messing
with my son,
you know, I'm always going
to be there on Gabriel's side.
[Stefany] I think we gravitate
to each other
because we've developed
that strong connection
from the beginning
as friends, you know.
[Stefany] He's always
hanging out in the room
with Billy
and everyone's up there
and I don't want to get
him upset.
I don't want to get you upset.
You gotta draw that line
or nothing else will
really develop.
At this point, Gabriel is just
being a [bleep].
That's not really my style.
I have done more than my part,
um, at just respect
them boundaries
and respecting when
it's my time and when
it's not my time.
I know Gabriel feels
threatened by me.
And I will feel threatened
by me, too.
I'm thinking of waking up
at five o'clock
in the morning.
- You are?
- [Ryan] Yes. I am.
My plan. You should wake up
and you should come see, like,
- the sunrise
and all the lights...
- At five thirty?
I can get up at five.
What time is it now?
- Ten fifteen.
- [Stefany] Oh.
- [Ryan] Yeah.
- You're not going to wake up.
Wanna bet?
- [Stefany] No.
No. As a matter of fact,
let's make a bet.
Gabriel can't come to your
room for one solid day.
[laughs]
Oh, my God!
- I get a full day.
- [Stefany laughing]
- Why is Gabriel in this bet?
- Huh?
- 'Cause.
- [Stefany] You're so...
[Ryan] It's a bet. It's a bet.
I get a full day
of communication.
He hangs out with Billy.
I mean, that's fine.
Billy gets to hang out
with him.
Both Gabriel and Ryan
are great guys.
But right now, I feel a little
pressured by Ryan.
I'm not really sure
how to respond
to a situation like this.
Making a bet with me to keep
Gabriel away, it just makes
me feel uncomfortable.
I think it could be a little
bit manipulative.
- Okay. I'll be up at five.
You have your bet.
- All right.
Gabriel gets no time
for 24-hours
and he can't-- he can't come
in the room. You get it?
[both laughing]
[Ryan] I make a silly bet
with Stefany,
we'll go watch the sunset
or something like that,
very early, five o'clock,
if you're not up, though,
you have to last 24-hours
without Gabriel.
I think the odds are stacked
in my favor.
[Stefany] Bed-time...
I got to get up at five
or else...
[Ryan laughs]
You're so bad.
[Ryan] Ain't I terrible?
Billy and I had a great
first date.
And now, he's setting up this,
uh, romantic hot tub session
in Pola and Jose's room,
so his mom can't be creeping
in on us.
- Hey...
- [Billy] Hi.
- [Kelle] Oh, it's less
than cold.
- [laughs]
[Kelle] The way I love it.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. It's so hot.
Whoa!
[Billy] It's getting
warmer, though.
I have candles all lined up.
- [Kelle] Yeah.
- And everything.
But the wind kept
blowing them out.
[both laughing]
[Billy] 'Cause I can't [bleep]
[bleep] wait.
[laughing]
It was like so nice
and pretty, like, there on--
[Kelle] I'm really hoping
that I get to see
if his size of his [bleep]
is real big.
[laughs]
[Billy speaking]
This hot tub
is freezing and...
unfortunately the only other
hot tub I could use is...
the one in our suite.
I don't really like the idea
of bringing someone
back to my room
with my mom being around,
but what else am I supposed
to do?
[Kelle] Oh, my--
[screams]
[laughs]
[both laughing]
I think anyone that is able
to laugh about themselves
is definitely someone
that I would want to date.
Like, if you take yourself
too seriously, like...
that's no good for me.
Why are you so far away?
You scared your mom's going
to come in?
I feel like I'm a teenager
again with Billy,
sneaking around the whole
house hiding, from his mom.
Billy's definitely going to be
put in time out after this.
Sorry, Mom.
[laughs]
- Whose are these?
- [Billy laughs]
- [Billy]
[Kelle and Billy laughing]
[indistinct conversation]
Yo...
- [laughs]
- Where?
In your room.
No. I'm gonna go in there.
- No. Don't.
- [Ryan] No. No. No. You can't.
- [Gabriel] No. No. Don't.
- [Ryan] You can't mess up
their ...
[Ryan speaking]
There is no way I'm gonna let
Kelle corrupt Billy.
I don't know if she's just
trying to push my buttons
or what her deal is.
But, yeah. Definitely,
definitely not here.
Not in my suite.
I'm gonna be like,
you gotta go.
Billy.
Oh, yeah.
Really? In our sauna?
Don't you have your own room?
Whether she likes it or not,
Billy and I are turning up
the heat.
Tonight, we're sleeping
in the same bed
and she needs to stop [bleep]
blocking him.
[indistinct chatter]
[doorbell rings]
[all screaming]
It just got real.
No. No.
[Stefany] Oh, yeah.
Kelle, you got to go.
[Kelle] We just got here.
Well, come in.
[Stefany] No. I'll be back.
[Kelle] That's okay.
Don't come back. We're fine.
Oh! That's your mom.
[laughs]
Stefany's popping into
the sauna unannounced,
I feel like it's a little
bit ridiculous
since her son is, like,
in his late 20's.
I know you all live together,
but do you not knock?
Whether she likes it or not,
Billy and I are turning up
the heat.
Tonight, we're sleeping
in the same bed
and she needs to stop [bleep]
blocking him.
[Gabriel] Where's Billy?
Billy!
Your new step-dad's here.
You are?
[Gabriel] Yeah.
What is?
- You're not gonna wake up
at five.
- [Stefany] At five?
[Stefany laughs]
[Gabriel] You're joking.
Someone attractive,
being controlling and stuff,
I felt like Ryan was
kind of being
a little controlling.
Like, telling Stefany,
wake up at 5:00 a.m.
If you don't, you can't be
around Gabriel for 24-hours.
And I was like, that's such
a weird way of looking
at things.
I don't want to be
an overbearing mom.
But I just...
don't like the fact that
Kelle's like six-feet away
from me in your bed.
I think I'm gonna be sleeping
with one eye open tonight.
I think you're being a little
bit too overprotective.
[Billy] Please don't
wake up at five?
I swear to God, if you do
this it's dumb.
- It's like giving--
- [Billy] It's so dumb.
Billy, isn't it giving
into it, too?
[Billy] Yeah. That's so dumb.
Maybe, she likes it.
[bleep]
[Stefany laughs]
Excuse me?
Turn it off.
I'm not waking. I can't have
an alarm go off at five.
[sighs]
[Kelle snoring]
Kelle had been drinking
- Yes.
- and she started hiccupping,
- [laughs] Yes.
- she started snoring
really loud.
So loud.
[Kelle snoring]
I was, like, in my mom's bed,
like, as a little kid.
It like, brought back
memories, like,
hiding from the monster.
[both laugh]
[snoring]
Me and Stefany, we made
a small bet.
I wake up this morning,
go upstairs...
[knocking at door]
[Ryan] Of course,
she doesn't answer.
If I'm just being transparent,
the way I stack the bet is...
I still get the time with
you if you wake up on time.
But if you lose, I still get
the time with you, regardless.
Let's see if Stefany
will pay up.
- Hi, Shannan.
- [Shannan] Hi.
What are you up to?
[Billy] Just rinsing out my...
- glass.
- [Shannan] Having your
afternoon beverage?
Yeah.
You look nice.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- How was your date?
[Shannan] Oh, that's what
I wanted to talk to you about.
'Cause I had a really nice
time with Jose.
I know that, you know,
you guys talk or whatever,
like, can you, like,
shed any light on, like,
who he might be really
interested in?
Is he your, uh,
number one prospect?
He is. But I need him to know
I'm different than
everybody else.
- Do you know what I mean?
- [Billy] Yeah. You don't want
to feel that on--
Yeah. I think he's like that
with, like, everyone.
I haven't had too much
of a conversation
with him about that.
- I think Jose is kind of just
really suave.
- [Stefany] So just charming.
- Yeah.
- And kind of...
- A charmer.
- Charming everyone,
and kind of just,
- uh, planting his seed
in every department.
- [laughs]
- Uh...
- Oh, my gosh.
I think he's just being
Rico Suave.
Oh, [bleep]
Let me just put it out there.
You know, I kind of heard
you, you know, had a nice
time with Kelle.
[laughs]
[Shannan] So, I'm like,
I was trying to figure out
what is it that, you know,
would make you click
with older women.
And I think last time
just happened.
- Um... we...
- Yeah. What happened?
- We got together
in the sauna and--
- Are you serious?
- Really?
- [Billy] Yeah. We we had
a great time.
- Oh, my God.
- [Billy] Yeah.
Like, together, together?
Not-- Yeah.
Did she keep her hands
to herself?
- [Billy stammers]
- I don't worry about you.
- [laughs]
- [Billy] We kind of...
- We were snuggling, and, uh...
- [Shannan] Uh-huh.
Is that all y'all were doing?
What I was hoping for...
was just to be able
to figure out how to get
to the next level.
Or maybe you take
the initiative.
Like, you go in for what
you want,
- Mmm. You think so?
- and kind of see how he reacts
to that.
Maybe just go for it.
- You know what?
That's a good approach.
- [Billy] Yeah.
- [Shannan] I like that.
I sing and I have my own band.
It's called April Jayne
and The Players.
[all cheering]
Like... like all of you.
And when we go back to L.A.,
- I play on Sunset Strip,
- [Soyoung] I'm coming.
- [Charlene] Awesome.
- all over, like, Hollywood,
different places.
You guys have to come.
- Yeah.
- We sure have to.
[Jimmy] I'm gonna
bring everybody.
My musicians are, mwah.
- [Jose] Back stage passes?
- Yes. Back stage
passes, autographs...
- [man 4] All right.
- [indistinct chatter]
[doorbell rings]
[all screaming]
What the hell is going on?
- [all cheering]
- No.
It just got real.
Okay.
It's time for some sex ed.
Since older women definitely
are more advanced
in the bedroom,
we can teach...
- [scoffs]
- a few things.
[both laughing]
[Shannan] Demonstrate
your go-to foreplay technique
on one of these fruits.
[Gabriel] Okay.
[all exclaiming]
Because...
[laughs]
[Stefany] I'm out. I can't
sit there.
[Jose] Go, go, go.
Today is the day that
I'm gonna make Jose
to be my man.
[Jose] Having her by my side,
definitely brought
us closer together.
[Shannan] Don't tell me
you like hanging out
with my son
but you're sleeping
with somebody else's son.
There are mixed signals
going both ways
- because what's happening...
- There's not.
He's talking to me
with his mom.
I think your feelings are hurt
because she doesn't like you.
Then why did she kiss
me on the beach,
telling me that she doesn't
[bleep] with you [bleep].
Ryan, you're so disrespectful.
- You're a liar. No. No. You--
- I'm too old to be dealing
with this.