[April J] Previously
on MILF Manor,
Ladies, where's
all the men at?
I think it's my time
to find love. I really do.
Are we looking for love?
Are we looking for romance?
All of my moments
have led me to this one.
You're the baby.
And you're gonna be 22, right?
I'm gonna be 22.
- Whoo!
- [laughs]
April is the woman
who immediately caught my eye.
Maybe I could show her
what it's like
with a younger man.
He's not going anywhere
near my mother.
It's time to play
"Wall of Secrets."
"I slept
with my son's best friend."
That's unacceptable.
"I had a seven-woman orgy."
Could that be my mom?
My secret is,
I slept with your best friend.
[all exclaiming]
This one hurts deep. This one
I did not see coming at all.
I didn't expect this at all.
I'm hoping he will forgive me.
Have you ever dated
older women?
I've had my eye on Jose
from day one.
I'm definitely going for it.
- Pola.
- Yes?
I'm taking your son out
on a date.
When?
Kelle is not
the type of girl for Jose.
I'm 100% sure.
[in Spanish]
[Kelle] I don't know
what they're talking about.
- Maybe they're talking
about us.
- Yeah.
- No speaking in Spanish!
We don't know.
- I heard...
The majority doesn't know
what you're saying.
She becomes like fire.
- You're excluding people
is what you're doing.
- [Pola] No!
- No.
- She's shouting at me,
just like...
Hopefully, you're gonna
leave Kelle just, by the side.
[bleeping]
I'm being greedy right now.
I want a pancake, too,
but I already have
a quesadilla,
which is a bread.
Wow. I ate a pancake
and a half, almost, too,
and I'm feeling like
it's too much carbs right now.
[Kelle] Last night,
with Pola and Stefany,
there was
tensions running hot.
Speaking Spanish
after I asked them to stop?
It's like, hello?
I'm sorry,
should I tell you in Spanish,
just shut the [bleep] up ?
[chuckles]
Just say that in Spanish.
Callate.
[chuckles]
Honestly, I really am
over the whole
speaking Spanish thing.
I could care less.
If they want
to keep speaking it,
keep speaking it.
If they want to stop,
they'll stop.
They know how I feel.
I'm over it.
I'm definitely
going to apologize,
and bury the hatchet,
so we can move on.
Oh, there she is.
[Stefany] Hey, what's up?
You ready to finish
what we started last night?
- Girl, you're...
What's up?
- I'm just kidding.
- Aw!
- I love you.
I love you, too.
No Spanish talk, right?
[chuckles]
You're silly.
I don't know if Kelle's
genuine this morning.
Maybe she's just trying
to get closer to our sons.
I think at this point,
I just might
keep my guard up,
a little bit,
just to see what
this is all about.
I'll teach you.
Before we leave,
you're gonna learn it all.
- [Kelle] Perfect. I love you.
- Mamacita.
- Say mamacita.
Soy una mamacita.
Soy yo mamacita.
[Stefany chuckles]
[laughs]
All right, girl.
Literal, no. No, no.
No, no, no. Of course.
When she came close to me,
I thought
she was gonna scream again.
Good morning.
- I apologize for last night.
- [Pola] No, don't worry.
Kelle apologizing
made me realize
that she is actually
smart enough
to recognize her mistakes,
but at this point,
I'm also open
to getting to know
the other women in the villa.
[Pola] I'm watching Kelle,
because I just want
to make sure
everything is fine,
and everyone is good.
I watch myself.
I know. I know.
Bam.
[chuckles]
Cheers to Spanish speaking.
[Kelle] Do you know what?
The funny part is,
is it's my fault,
because I actually took
Spanish classes, like...
I started taking it,
and then I quit,
and now, you know what?
- It bit me on the ass.
- Yeah.
So what happens if you meet
this, like, hot stud
that only speaks Spanish?
[Kelle] Then we just
make love. [laughs]
How are you doing, king?
Bro, I'm doing good.
[Gabriel] The secrets
and [bleep] , you know,
kind of hit home for people,
and I was like, "Damn.
It might be a little annoying
finding out
your mom did that[bleep] .
I was just checking in,
if you wanted
to talk about it,
or something, you know?
The most shocking secret,
for sure,
was Jimmy finding out his mom
[bleep] his best friend.
Did that kind of
bother you a little bit?
Oh, yeah,
it bothers me, obviously.
It's odd.
For one, I didn't know,
for two, it's supposed to,
apparently, like,
my best friend,
and for three,
now everybody knows.
Imagine you in my shoes,
you know what I mean?
[Gabriel] I'd be
pretty pissed.
If you made a mistake,
or something,
when I was younger, whatever,
but for you to, like,
tell me in front of strangers
would kind of be,
like, embarrassing.
I definitely would have said
something to my son
if I was going to reveal that
to a group of people.
- [Jimmy] Come on.
- I would probably fly home.
- I'm not kidding.
- [Jimmy] Yeah.
- I would fly home.
Yeah.
[Gabriel] I think maybe
he should talk to Soyoung,
because that's a bomb to drop.
If you just want to have
a conversation that's private,
I'm always here to talk.
I'm just trying to get
a little lit tonight.
I think that
revealing the secret
was very hard for me.
I don't know how
you feel towards me.
Are you saying
you don't know how I feel?
How would you feel,
is the question.
I'm angry.
I don't know how
to even look at you,
and talk to you
in a sensible manner, where
I can be your son right now.
I feel like
you didn't treat me
like your son.
Well, I am so sorry.
I never even think that way,
that I'm put in your shoes.
- [Gabriel] But, cheers.
- Cheers.
- I love you.
- I love you, dude.
- [kisses]
- I love you.
[Shannan] Bye.
Vamonos!
All right, we know.
Just kidding.
Adios.
As yesterday's winners
of the "Wall of Secrets"
challenge,
Ryan, Joey, and myself
got to choose
whoever we want
to take out on a date tonight.
Stefany!
[all cheering]
I choose Pola.
I'm going with April tonight.
- [all exclaiming]
- [all cheering]
[Gabriel] I'm excited
for my first date.
I get to go out of the villa,
and I get alone time
with Stefany.
I've never been
on a double date
with my mom before.
[laughs]
- It definitely doesn't seem
like my mom's vibe.
- I'm with Joey.
He's 20.
And he's such a gentleman,
which I really like in a man.
[festive
Mexican music playing]
Whoo-hoo!
[Joey] I picked April
because I love her vibe.
I love her energy.
Not only does April have
a beautiful face,
beautiful body,
she has a great personality,
but she's also very wise.
She could teach me
many things.
It's very attractive
that she has
a lot of life experience.
[chuckles]
Welcome
to La Miserable Mezcaleria.
Take a seat.
Vamos.
Stefany caught my eye
because she just seems
so sweet, and I think
she's super pretty.
She seems like
a well put together gal,
so I could definitely,
you know,
be interested in that.
Thank you.
I picked Pola because
she's very nice on the eyes,
personality-wise,
very warm,
very inviting,
very exciting.
Banging body, too.
[waiter] I will explain to you
a little bit
about mescal today.
What you have today
are three different mescals
from three different parts
of Mexico.
You have also
a little bit of crickets.
Yes, crickets,
edible crickets.
- You can peel it...
- [gags]
[waiter] ...and eat it,
that is, removing the legs...
- [Pola] Ugh!
- [waiter] ...or you can
eat it whole.
[Joey] It was actually
the very first time
I've seen crickets
on a dinner table like that.
[chuckles]
If I'm gonna try them
with anyone, it'll be April J.
- How do you like them?
- I didn't realize
that they were so, like,
- crickety.
- [Joey laughing]
Totally, yeah!
They're so crickety.
Ahhh!
- [both laugh]
- God!
Come on, you have to.
[Pola]
I really enjoy that Ryan
is more secure about himself,
and I knew he was more mature.
It's good that he asked me out
on this date.
- [laughs]
- It's disgusting!
Salud, everyone.
Salud.
- [Stefany chuckling]
Oh, no, no!
- [spits]
[Stefany] What happened?
[Gabriel] Open your mouth,
close your eyes.
Ahhh! [chuckles]
Gabriel's throwing crickets,
and, you know,
getting grossed out,
and kind of being immature
about the situation.
It comes off
a bit disrespectful
to act that way.
I'm not seeing
what Stefany's seeing in him.
I'm not understanding
how he's gonna find
an older woman that
will actually be interested
in seriously dating him,
just being that childish.
From what I'm seeing,
she's sitting with a man-baby.
[Joey] Hey!
That's what you get
for asking my mom on a date!
- [bleeping] [laughs]
- [Joey] Hey!
[Gabriel] Joey's
a little sly guy,
and now, he's trying
to hit on my mom,
and it's not sitting right
with me.
It's not sitting pretty.
[Joey] Wow.
- Hey.
- [chuckling] Calm down.
- You're the most intriguing
person in the house.
- Aw!
I want to be with Jose.
- I love my son.
- Okay.
It is a bit of mama's boy
going on with Jose and Pola.
[Gabriel] Have you
ever thought
you could date, like,
a younger guy?
Yeah. For sure.
[Gabriel] What do you like
about me?
Your vibe,
it's so, you know...
I think it's the energy.
I love your eyes.
Hmm?
They're cute.
[Stefany] How about you?
Why did you pick me
to go out on a date?
I thought you were
the prettiest. Like, my type.
Thank you.
It would be fun to actually
get to know you a little bit.
I make music. I'm an artist.
I do modeling as well.
I travel a lot, so...
I'd say my ideal girl needs
to be kind of well-rounded,
intelligent, really just
a happy, positive person.
What's your, like,
best date idea?
- Best, if you had to come up
with a dream date.
- I'm really simple.
I think, just like a nice,
I think, conversation,
and some candles.
I feel like talking to Stefany
the first five minutes,
I could already tell
she's independent,
she's strong, so I'm
definitely interested in that.
To getting to know each other.
Yes.
- Salud.
[Stefany] I've never dated
anyone like Gabriel.
He's stylish,
he's spontaneous,
He's very funny, outgoing.
He just says it how it is.
I am excited to see
what God has in store for us.
- Oh, you're the best.
- [exhales]
[April J] What are the effects
of these crickets?
- Are there some type of...
- [Joey] Yes.
- Are they aphrodisiacs, or...
- Psychedelic? [chuckles]
- [April J] What is it?
- [Joey] I mean, I'm assuming
they bring good luck,
and good love.
[chuckles]
[April J] Maybe.
[Gabriel] Joey's
a little sly guy,
and now, he's trying
to hit on my mom,
and it's not sitting right
with me.
It's not sitting pretty.
I would have never thought
that I would be here
with such a beautiful woman.
I think I'm
the oldest mom in the house,
and Joey is
the youngest man in the house,
but Joey's so sweet,
and complimentary,
and sensitive.
He's actually acting
more like a man
than most men twice his age.
Just because, you know,
my license says this,
and your license says that...
[Joey] Mmm-hmm.
I'm sure you have
a license, right?
[both laugh]
[Gabriel] Mom!
How's your date going?
[chuckles]
Oh, it's going great.
Don't get her too wasted.
- I'm trying to have
my date. "Mom!"
- [laughs]
- [Gabriel] Mom,
it's about my date.
-"Mom!"
- [Gabriel] it's
about our date, okay?
-"Mom!"
[Joey] "Mom!" "Mom!"
I'm not intimidated at all
by having Gabriel around.
Well, I think Gabriel's
honestly annoyed with me.
He doesn't like whatever
is going on at my table.
That boy better watch out.
I'm gonna be his papa one day.
Hey!
- That's what you get
for asking my mom on a date!
- [Joey] Hey!
[bleeping]
- [bleeping] [laughs]
- [Joey] Hey!
- [Stefany chuckling]
Calm down.
- [Ryan] Wow.
I'm tired of watching
Gabriel be corny.
You know? I just want to
kind of be in my own vibes,
right now, with Pola,
and just really, you know,
experience this date
for what it can be,
so I was,
"It's time to take a walk."
- All right,
let's walk, and talk.
- Let's go.
Thanks. You don't want
to take the empanada?
- I'm all set.
- [laughs]
[Ryan] Obviously,
I think Pola's attractive.
I think her energy
is much younger than her age.
[Pola] Vamos.
- [Ryan] Okay.
- [chuckles]
[in Spanish]
That is the reason why I want
to get to know Pola better.
I'm not gonna have crickets.
I'm never gonna do that.
Never, ever. Never.
- Well, you missed out.
It was so much fun.
- It's fine. It's fine.
It's okay with me.
So now, anyways,
on a serious note,
I brought you out tonight
because to me, personally,
- you're the most intriguing
person in the house.
- Aw!
[Ryan] You have
a lot of confidence,
I think
you're absolutely gorgeous,
and I think, most importantly,
internally
you're a great person,
- and that's extremely
attractive to me.
- Thank you.
When he looks at me, like,
he feels really confident,
and that becomes really sexy.
So, in your eyes,
what's your purpose
at the house?
Right now?
I really want
to enjoy my company.
[Ryan] Okay.
I really love myself.
So, I want to be
with myself first,
than being
with anybody else.
[Ryan] Okay.
Then, I want to be
with Jose.
- I love my son.
- Okay.
Jose is my guy, but it is...
It is a bit of mama's boy
going on with Jose and Pola.
[Pola] And then,
I'm really open to anything.
So, let me ask you this.
So far...
- Yeah.
- ...out of all
of your dates, so far...
This has been really good.
- This has been good?
- I like mescal, yes.
- Don't give me
the friend hand on the date.
- [laughs]
Don't you Jimmy me.
Pola, to me,
has the most question marks.
Is she here to date?
You know,
'cause I am here to date,
and you really have to be
on the same page
with somebody to see
if you can
further progress with them.
[kissing]
[kisses]
[Ryan] If Pola is gonna
continue to be guarded,
obviously I gotta
keep it moving.
Um, it's like the McRib
at McDonald's, you know?
Like, "limited time only,"
you know? [laughs]
- All right, come on.
- That was great.
- [guys laughing]
- Salud.
Salud.
[Gabriel] "Salud,
salud, salud!"
- [Jose] That's my mama.
- [Gabriel laughs]
So, are you loving it here?
Yeah. I'm super excited.
I'm a very open-minded person.
- [Kelle] Yeah.
- Very relaxed.
"Go with the flow"
type of person.
[Kelle] I'm open
to anything, too.
We have to be.
Even though
everything was great
going to Mushroom Rock
with Jose on our first date,
after the blowup,
now I feel like
he's avoiding me
like the plague, so...
I think that Jose
is definitely a mama's boy,
for sure.
I mean, if he's not going
to make an effort,
and he's just gonna let me go,
then I'm gonna
keep moving forward,
so that's exactly
what I'm gonna do.
So, now I'm gonna see
what Billy's got going on.
Have you dated younger before?
Yeah.
Do you prefer younger,
or older, around your age?
[Kelle chuckles]
I feel like younger guys
are a lot more open,
and they don't have a lot of,
um, constraints, I think,
on their thought process.
They don't, like,
overthink things
because of stuff that happened
to them in the past.
- They're just more free
with, like...
- [Billy] Yeah.
...who they are,
and I feel like a lot of times
they have more direction
on where they want to go.
What about you?
Um...
I don't really see
too much of an age thing.
Age isn't really
a problem for me.
Just like you,
connection is very important,
the right chemistry.
[Kelle] The one thing
that I really love,
that's a big turn-on for me,
is a guy that puts in effort,
and that actually shows
interest in me,
so the fact
that Billy's actually showing
interest in me, I'm kind of
open to exploring,
you know, to see
if there's anything there.
- [Ryan] What's that?
The pinot?
- You want one?
Where's mine?
[Ryan] It's coming.
- [chuckles]
- [Ryan] I'm
about to bring it over.
- Thank you.
- You're killing yourself
that way, for them.
Oh!
[Stefany] Thank you.
- [Ryan] Absolutely.
- [Stefany] You're so nice.
[Ryan] I try to be.
- Cheers.
- [Ryan] Cheers.
I feel like the date with Pola
goes pretty well,
but I am here to date,
so I'm kind of shifting,
you know, my interest
at this point toward Stefany.
Hopefully, I can show her
something different
than she was experiencing
at the table with Gabriel.
Do you date women with kids?
At my age,
I'm used to it now,
but like, it's kind of, like,
the inconvenience
- of trying to plan with you,
and spend time with you.
- [Stefany] Yeah.
If I really like you,
I'm gonna make the time.
[Ryan] I think Stefany
is just naturally sexy,
and extremely
well put together.
She's definitely
an eye talker,
and that gets me every time.
Even though Stefany is older,
she kind of has, like,
a young appeal.
She's obviously
an attractive woman.
Do you do online dating?
I've done it before.
Do you do FaceTime
before you meet them?
- [Ryan] Uh...
- Ah!
I learned my lesson with that
- a couple times before, so...
[chuckles]
- [Stefany] Yes!
I FaceTime like, all right,
you swiped? Let's FaceTime.
- Like, yeah, let me see you.
- [Stefany chuckling] Right.
Ryan is 30,
and actually, it works for me,
because our communication
seemed to be
on the same level,
because he's the one
that's closest to my age,
and I felt
chemistry with Ryan.
[Gabriel] I don't know Ryan,
but I feel like
based off the first day
or two days,
you know, he's hitting on
more than one girl,
so I feel like that might show
that, okay, yeah,
he's a little player type.
I'm someone who...
I don't really
get jealous that easily,
but I feel like Stefany and I
have something going,
so I feel like he kind of
needs to uh, you know,
stay out the way!
[chuckles]
I am a very good kisser.
Would you like
to test it out?
Billy's cute, but, um,
his game is super weak.
You have food in your mouth!
Now you're gonna kiss me
with food...
[chuckles]
Sorry, not happening.
[Billy] I give up.
[laughs]
[Kelle] I think
Billy's attractive.
He's not necessarily my type.
The type of guys
I normally date
would be super chatty,
super outgoing, but I mean,
that's why we're here,
to get to know other people
that we don't fit into, like,
what we think is our type,
to get to know other people
outside of the norm.
These are so good.
[Kelle] What's going through
your little head?
[Billy] So, I've been told
I'm a very good kisser,
but I need someone to tell me
- if that is true or not.
- [laughing] Oh, my God!
Would you like to test it out?
- I mean, right now?
- Yes.
- Can you give me a minute?
- Okay.
Oh, my gosh,
and you're asking?
You're not supposed to ask.
You're supposed to, like,
in the moment, just, like,
- kind of do it.
- I'm a gentleman.
[Billy] I really like
being around Kelle,
because she really brings out
a youthful side to me,
and she also makes me laugh,
which is very important to me.
[Kelle] You have
food in your mouth!
Now you're gonna kiss me
with food...
Billy's cute,
and his dry sense of humor
is funny,
but, um,
his game is super weak.
[Billy] Hold that thought.
[laughs]
[Kelle] Sorry, pick.
It's me or the carrot.
Not both.
Not happening.
So weird.
[Billy] I give up.
- You judged me on that.
- [chuckling] You gave up
already?
Yeah.
You're so funny.
I definitely didn't want
to eat your carrot.
[laughs]
[Billy] My first kiss
with Kelle, I would have liked
if it had gone on longer,
but it was
the first kiss,
so it was short and sweet.
Wait, what else is in here?
- [Kelle] Knowing you?
Condoms for sex on the beach.
- [Billy laughs]
[chuckles]
The one I picked for Billy was
I've had sex in public
on the beach.
- Yeah.
- [all exclaiming]
You can't be trusted.
They don't really have
the right sized condoms
for me here.
[both chuckle]
What are you...
What are you saying, Billy?
Mmm.
[mumbles]
[Kelle] I wasn't
expecting this at all.
I think it's hot when a guy
is so confident
about his size of his penis.
It's like, maybe he has
this crazy, wild side
that even Stefany
doesn't know about.
Billy's definitely becoming
one of my favorites,
at this point.
- Cheers to an amazing date.
- Yeah.
- Many more to come, hopefully.
- [Kelle] Oh, okay.
♪ Let me love you ♪
[indistinct conversation]
Billy and I
had a good time today.
He's amazing. I love him.
He's really, really...
He's really sweet.
He said he has a big [bleep] .
How does it make you feel?
[sputtering]
[Kelle laughs]
[Stefany] Oh, my gosh, Kelle!
- [chuckles]
- He said that!
[laughs]
- Keep that
to yourself, please.
- [Kelle] No, dude!
If your son's, like,
spilling the beans,
- I just wanted to know,
did you know...
- Oh, my God.
[Kelle] ...that I know
that he might know...
[Stefany] Keep it PG, please.
I honestly do not want
to hear about my son's
package.
I mean,
it really feels awkward
to hear her
talk to me about this.
It's crazy,
you're saying that.
She probably already knows
that her son is hung.
I mean, it is her boy,
so she must know, right?
I don't want to know
any of that. [chuckles]
Well, now you know.
Okay, Kelle.
You heard it here first.
[upbeat Latin music playing]
Oh, gosh. I think
there's only one person here
that I think
is actually sexual,
and that would know
what to do,
and take the bull
by the horns, is Ryan.
- He's got the most sex--
- [laughing] Was it
the seven-person orgy?
- Was it the orgy?
- [both laugh]
[cell phone beeps]
Guys, I have a text!
What does it say?
It says, "Moms and sons,
it's time to get moving.
We want you
to come up with a dance
that best communicates love,
passion, and desire.
You all will be the judges,
and the duo
with the most votes
- wins a special double date...
- [Gabriel] Ooh!
...to a Latin dance club."
- [all exclaiming]
- [all cheering]
We got this, Pola.
Oh, no!
- If they have color,
they're gonna win this.
- [laughs]
No doubt.
Harrison, you feel confident?
- How do you feel?
- Oh yeah, I'm feeling good.
- We got this.
- I think we got this
in the bag.
Yeah. We're gonna have
so much fun.
Oh, I'm gonna bring it.
It's Magic Mike time.
Yeah!
- [Jimmy] Forward.
- [Soyoung] Roll forward.
- Boom, boom, boom, boom.
- Dit, dit, dit, dit.
[both] Dum, dum,
dum, dum.
[Jimmy] No.
You did it wrong again.
The secret really
kind of, like,
disrupted me and my mom's
energy together, so
it makes it very difficult
to work with somebody,
so you can only imagine
how awkward this is for me.
- Dit, dit, dit, dit.
- No!
You gotta go right
with the four count.
[Soyoung] I don't feel
his heart in it,
'cause I know Jimmy.
He's not putting out 100%.
It's sad.
No. See, that's...
[both] ...one, two,
three, four.
[Jimmy] I want to win,
but it's hard
when you have two people
trying to dance,
and move together,
and everything
is like a locomotive,
and there's, like,
something broken
in our machine right now,
and for us to go
and win this competition
is gonna be a real challenge.
[both laugh]
[Stefany in Spanish]
I don't think he knows what
he wants to do with Stefany.
I think
Gabriel likes attention...
...but I think that
she's interested in me 100%.
[all chuckling]
[Shannan] Let's go!
[Ryan] Coming through.
[chuckling]
Let's get this party started.
Yeah!
[Kelle] For this week's
challenge,
all the mothers and sons
need to come up
with a dance routine
that communicates
passion and desire.
We're all gonna judge
each other,
and the duo that wins
gets to pick two people
to go on a date
to a salsa club tonight.
- [Shannan] All right!
- [Ryan] Ready?
All right, cool.
- [Shannan] Let's go!
- Let's go! With us!
[all cheering]
[Shannan] I am very much so
a dance-y person.
I love, love, love to dance.
- [dance music playing]
- I love it!
[Ryan] We gotta
get my mom a date.
If you knew what I know,
it's over.
Shannan goes crazy
on the dance floor.
I'm trying to say that
right now.
- [all exclaiming]
- [all cheering]
- [Shannan]
On the dance floor...
- [Ryan] Yes.
...I'm unstoppable.
I do a little pop, pop
with the hip.
I don't have to say
a whole lot.
- [Ryan] Just standing there.
- [Shannan] It's all
about the movement,
so that's how I roll.
- Surprise attack,
that's what you're saying.
- Right.
- Okay.
- Lady in the street...
You finish the sentence.
[chuckles]
- [all exclaiming]
- [all cheering]
[Ryan] She's killing it.
She's putting
her moves on display.
At this point, we got
a good shot to win this.
[both laugh]
[all applauding]
Come back up.
- [chuckles]
- [all laughing]
[dance music playing]
[all exclaiming]
- [all laughing]
- [all exclaiming]
Me and my mom
are super competitive
- in everything we do.
- Always been, right?
[Jimmy] We want to win,
so our minds just synchronize
on the spot.
- [laughs]
- [all applauding]
[Jimmy] After the challenge,
it really hit me,
and I realized,
I'm not mad at you.
I'm just mad at the situation
that it ever happened,
but it's really okay.
- You know,
there's no hard feelings.
- [Soyoung] Yeah.
[Jimmy] I've had
a great life.
I've been happy in my
and our experience of life,
so there's nothing
to really be sad about.
I'm so sorry,
- everything that upset you.
- [Jimmy] No, it's...
- It's okay, um...
- That's past, and I hope
that you forgive me.
- I do.
- Give me a hug.
- I love you.
- Everything's okay.
- Ooh!
Sorry.
[Latin American music playing]
Whoo!
[all cheering]
[all exclaiming]
[Joey] I got my eye on April.
She's got the energy up,
so hopefully,
I can take her hand,
and get grooving
on the dance floor.
- [music stops]
- Ahhh!
[all cheering]
That's so sexy!
I can't wait to see what
Magic Mike got for us.
[all laughing]
- [all applauding]
- All right, guys.
[Harrison] When I hear
people cheering,
I feel good for my mom,
that she's actually able
to share this moment with me.
- [dance music playing]
- [all exclaiming]
[ululates]
I got a little too excited.
I forgot it was a competition!
[chuckles]
- [women screaming]
- [all exclaiming]
The shirt comes off,
and all the ladies go crazy!
[women screaming]
Harrison? Mmm.
He made me hot.
[women screaming]
Whew! Lord, have mercy!
That was awesome!
- There! [chuckles]
- Put your shirt on.
That's smooth!
Lethal abs!
[Kelle] Harrison
taking his shirt off
was probably
one of the highlights
of the house
since we've been here.
I wonder how much
I can bribe Harrison
to give me a lap dance?
Okay, guys.
It's time to pick.
So, our top pick is
Magic Mike and Charlene!
[all cheering]
We actually went with
- Harrison and Charlene.
- [all exclaiming]
- We the ladies!
- [all cheering]
So, I didn't have
much of a choice,
- after my mother's
natural reactions...
- [laughs]
- ...so...
- ...Charlene and Harrison.
- [all exclaiming]
- [all cheering]
- [Ryan] There you go.
- [Shannan] Charlene
and Magic Mike!
[Jose]
The winner is...
Drum roll.
[all patting hands]
[Jose] ...Harrison
and Charlene!
[all cheering]
[Charlene] It feels amazing.
It took me time,
but I finally get to go out
on a date.
For my date,
I'm gonna ask Jose.
- Oh, Jose!
- [all applauding]
Thank you, Charlene.
[Charlene] I think
Jose is hot.
Who knows
what tonight will bring,
with all of that spice
on the dance floor?
[all chanting] Jose, Jose!
[Stefany] Harrison just won,
and all the ladies
are like,
"Pick me! Pick me!"
For my date, I'm gonna ask
Stefany to come dancing
with me tonight.
- [all exclaiming]
- [all cheering]
[Gabriel] At first,
I am, like, a little annoyed.
I felt like I kind of
already let her know
that I'm interested in
at least developing
a relationship with Stefany,
so I feel like, you know,
I've kind of made
my presence apparent,
so I'm pretty secure in that,
and I don't think
anyone's gonna catch her eye
as much as I did.
[Ryan] I had been talking
to Stefany
when Harrison picks her,
so it sucks,
because we're developing
a connection,
and that chemistry,
and I really had plans
in my head.
You know, getting to know her,
and like,
yo, we're gonna go
on a date,
then we'll kind of see
where these things go,
so I was not prepared
for that, at all.
[all cheering]
- [Jose] Estamos listos?
Are we ready, or what?
- [Stefany] Si.
[Harrison] Yeah!
All ready to get
your little boogie on?
- Whoo-hoo!
- All right!
[Latin American music playing]
[Jose] I don't know
much about Charlene,
but I can tell that
she's interested
in getting to know me,
so I'm curious as well,
to getting to know her.
It's gonna be so nice.
We're doing it!
- Okay, okay.
We're gonna do it.
- Yeah.
- Show me something.
- Back.
- [Charlene] Okay.
- [both] Back.
[both] Back.
Hey, your mom
is learning very good, eh?
- Yeah.
- Let me tell you!
Ha! Ha!
- You're my date now,
so...[chuckles]
- Yeah, yeah. Excited.
My pleasure.
[Charlene] I'm feeling sexy,
I'm seeing Jose do the moves,
so that makes me
attracted to him.
Do it, do it! Go!
At that point, it's just about
the sexiness of the dance.
Nice! Oh, I get to spin
you too. Okay, sorry.
Come on, Harrison.
You got this.
- You got it.
- [Harrison] I'll try.
- [Stefany] Pretend
your mom's not here.
- [chuckles]
[Stefany chuckles]
[Harrison] I kept
looking over,
my mom was dancing with Jose,
I'm like,
"What am I doing right now
at the club with my mom?"
Wow. That was fun.
- Yeah.
- [Stefany] Was it awkward
- a little bit,
'cause your mom's there?
- Now awkward.
It was just, like,
she's over there
with a...[chuckles]
- [laughs]
- ...with some, you know,
somebody young.
Who do you think
you like most in the house?
In the house
that I vibe with?
Yeah, that you, like,
really vibe with.
It's crazy,
'cause I really like
- Soyoung's personality a lot.
- Yeah.
I just think
she's really cool.
Who are you
the most attracted to?
That would be Pola.
[Stefany] I thought
he was gonna say, "Oh, you."
But no, he actually named
other ladies.
Okay, then why am I
the one here with you?
If he had a connection
with someone else,
he should have gone with them,
and not brought me
on this date.
They seem to be
doing amazing.
Thank you for bringing me
out on this date.
- You did great
on the dance floor, so...
- Thank you, thank you.
- [Charlene] I'm so used to
leading all the time, that--
- You are?
- Why?
- Yeah, because
I'm independent.
I have to do
everything for myself.
I don't really,
you know...
Who would I be following?
But no, but in dating, like,
people that
you've dated before,
you usually lead
the conversations, and the...
- [Charlene] Um...
- Or it's mixed?
No. I feel like
if I were to do that,
that I would lose interest.
[Jose] Why?
I don't know. I kind of...
Maybe I'm old-fashioned
in that way...
- Okay.
- ...where, in my life,
being single,
and a single mom,
and independent...
- Yeah.
- ...I always had to take care
of things, and business,
so it's like, when you're
always wearing the pants,
- or always having to, like,
take the bull by the horns...
- Yeah.
...I'd like to think
that it's nice
to be able to just, like,
let my hair down, and relax...
- Mmm.
- ...and feel like someone can
just lead the conversation.
I am tired
of being independent
in that sense of like, listen,
it's time for me to be able
to, like, sit back and relax.
I've had to be
the front-runner
for a long time now, so yeah,
I'm ready to let somebody else
take the wheel
for a little while.
Um, I see it
completely differently,
in dating, especially.
I see both as equals...
- Right.
- ...so part has
its own liberty, and...
- I mean, I get that.
- You know what I mean?
- And don't drive.
- But a woman needs to feel
a certain way.
If you say to me,
"Would you like to go out?"
that lets me know
you're interested.
- It's not that I would expect
a woman to approach at all.
- Right, right.
- It's that if she does...
- Yeah.
...I'll be surprised,
and I would say, like,
-"Okay," like, "That's cool."
- Yeah.
I think Jose was starting
to understand my perspective,
but at the same time,
part of me thinks
that deep down, it's not
that important to him.
Like, I don't think he really
gets where I'm coming from,
and what that means
from a woman.
Romantically, as a woman...
- [Jose] Uh-huh.
- ...I want to feel desired.
[Jose] We had a lot of fun,
but I think
that romantic chemistry
is not quite there.
- Salud?
- [Charlene] All right.
- Before we go, let's salud.
- [Charlene] Yes.
- [Jose] Gracias.
- One for the road.
- [chuckles]
- [Jose] Yes.
Would you have gone,
like, Latin dancing,
- or is that not your vibe?
- I would have went.
- Hell yeah.
- Yeah? Would you
have had fun?
- I would go. Yeah.
- That's an answer.
- That seems like
a cute date, huh?
- It's fun.
So, I feel like
Stefany's been going on dates,
and like, she's allowed to do
whatever she wants,
but then again,
I was kind of bummed,
just because for me,
personally,
I don't really have my eye
on anyone else.
Want some beer, maybe?
- What's happening?
- So, you went on a date
with Harrison.
- Yeah.
- [Charlene chuckles]
[Charlene] What's that mean
for you guys, yeah?
- Kind of wanted
to talk to you about it.
- [Charlene and Pola chuckle]
[Ryan] Gabriel's just doing
a little too much for me.
We didn't come in here
with ties already.
This is new energy.
We're getting to know
new people.
You don't know
what pair fits.
He's a smooth guy, huh?
Oh, my gosh.
[Ryan] I feel like
Gabriel lacks respect,
because every time
it's somebody else's turn
to get to know someone,
it's not your time
to infringe.
[both chuckle]
[Ryan] I don't think
he knows what
he wants to do with Stefany,
but I think
Gabriel likes attention,
and I think that
anything without him,
I think he wants to be in it.
[imitates slide whistle]
[chuckles]
[all laughing]
[Stefany in Spanish]
- Who, you and I?
- Yeah.
I do like Gabriel a lot,
but I'm a little confused,
at this point.
[Gabriel] I do not feel
threatened by Ryan,
because no one really has
a chance in here.
I think it's in the bag.
How do you feel about Gabriel?
More friends.
I think that she's interested
in me, 100%.
- [all exclaiming]
- [all laughing]
The conversations
that I've had
with Stefany so far,
I feel like I've peeled back
some layers with her.
I've gotten to know
her better,
but we haven't even been
on a date yet,
so I think this is
the perfect opportunity,
because it is
extremely important
for me to peel back layers.
With anybody
that I'm involved with,
I like to know
what I'm dealing with
before I get into it.
I would like to know
what I'm signing up for.
You got to read a contract
before you sign it.
- Who, you and I?
- Yeah.
- Okay, so...
- Come.
Oops.
[Stefany]
-"Come on," you know.
- [Stefany chuckles]
[Stefany] I do like
Gabriel a lot,
but I'm a little confused,
at this point,
because I jibe with Ryan.
He's a cool dude.
Why wouldn't I want to go
snorkeling with him?
[chuckling] Let's go.
Bye!
Ohhh!
[Gabriel] I do not feel
threatened by Ryan,
because me and Stefany
were definitely killing it.
We like each other.
I definitely think no one
really has a chance in here.
I think it's in the bag.
[Stefany] I haven't gone
snorkeling in, like, so long.
[Ryan] I'm excited
to go snorkeling,
because
the water's magnificent.
Like, the water's
beautiful here,
and it's even more exciting
to do it with a person
that you're interested in,
that's looking good.
No.
[Stefany] Ryan's definitely
looking out.
He's teaching me
how to snorkel.
I'm following his lead.
He makes me feel comfortable.
Just going with the flow.
So, he goes in for the kiss,
and it was just so sweet.
[chuckles]
[kisses]
[Stefany] This is so...
[Ryan] Stefany's
a pretty good kisser.
It's not an awkward kiss.
This kiss is meant to happen.
These lips and these lips work
when they come together.
Here's to great friendships,
and good times.
Good times.
[Stefany] Cheers.
So, are you enjoying yourself?
[Ryan] I am.
Like, I feel like
the first couple
of conversations we had
were like, very open.
I appreciate in general
how your conversation is,
and then, how
genuine you are.
Thanks for acknowledging that.
How do you feel
about the moms?
Well, you know,
there's a couple people
that I've had my eye on.
I was open with you.
You were one of those people.
I just felt like
it was a lot to
get some time with you,
- you know, like,
just because...
- Oh, because I was always
with Gabriel, you mean?
I mean, yeah, like,
how do feel about Gabriel now?
Honestly?
He's funny,
but I think...
I don't know.
We've hung out,
we've gone out on a date,
but it's just been fun,
like, more friends, I think.
I haven't...
I mean, he didn't...
He hasn't tried
to kiss me, or anything.
I think because Gabriel
makes me feel comfortable,
maybe it comes off that I'm
only, you know, open to him.
I think I like you the most,
because you're older.
- The older son.
- Right.
Yeah.
I feel like the other sons
are more like
-"friends" friends, I think.
- Mmm-hmm.
If that's the case, then...
- [Stefany] Mmm-hmm.
- ...based on this date
and wherever it goes,
- since I'm the first person
you kissed in the house...
- [Stefany] I know.
...rough question for you.
[sighs]
What do you think?
You know, I like
hanging out with you,
and I think
we've had a connection,
but we haven't had
enough time to spend
- time together.
- Yeah.
This was fun.
[Ryan] Based on
what Stefany tells me,
I think that
she's interested in me,
100%.
Now look, I'm gonna be
down for you,
but you gotta make time.
You know what I'm saying?
There's plenty more dates
where this came from,
in my eyes, with you.
Cheers to more dates, Ryan.
Cheers to more dates
with you, Stefany.
♪ I know all about it
You're my Cadillac love ♪
[Ryan] Gabriel thinks
he's sealed the deal
with Stefany,
but in my eyes, I mean,
I'm obviously the choice.
That's the bottom line.
[laughs]
- Are you comfy,
or are you falling?
- You're gonna... I'm...
- I'm perfect.
- Put your legs.
[Stefany] I am perfect!
You want to sit here, too?
Stefany, offer him a spot,
I'm out.
I know Gabriel feels
threatened by me,
and I would feel
threatened by me, too.
[Kelle] Billy and I
are turning up the heat.
Sorry, Mom.
I just don't like the fact
that Kelle's, like
six feet away from me,
in your bed.
I think you're being
a little bit
too overprotective.
And now, for the bad news.
- Ooh!
- Oh!
There is one mother
and one son going home.
- [gasps]
- [April J] Oh, no!
- [Pola] What the...
- [Shannan] No.
- [Pola] What?
- [Stefany] No.
- [Gabriel] Are you serious?
- I didn't think
anybody was going home.
- It's not a joke.
- Hey, show me
that thing it's in.
It just got real.
It's just shocking.
[Billy] It's serious, people.