Being here and seeing this
beautiful sunset and how
beautiful you look,
this is a really special
moment as well.
[Shannan] I feel like Jose may
give everyone
that kind of attention.
So, you don't know
if you're special.
I feel like I'm a teenager
again with Billy.
Sneaking around the whole
house, hiding from his mom.
No, I'm going to go in there.
There is no way I'm going
to let Kelle corrupt Billy.
Not in my suite.
[Stefany] I'm going to be
like, "You've got to go."
Really? In our sauna?
Oh, you're the baby.
You're going to be 22, right?
I'm going to be 22.
Oh!
April is the woman who
immediately caught my eye.
I would have never thought
that I would be here
with such a beautiful woman.
The new Ryan wants
to take me out.
[Gabriel] That's annoying.
Do you still love me?
[Ryan S] Stefany and Gabriel
really have a connection.
I'm not going to put
my eggs in that basket.
- Have you told Gabriel that...
- [Stefany] He knows!
- he's just a friend?
- He knows!
- You're lying.
- He and I are good friends.
This love triangle has just
gotten way out of hand.
He got mad because
you laying on the couch,
you were leaning over.
- [Gabriel] Are you
his girlfriend?
- No!
I haven't made a decision
with anybody here.
[Gabriel] Bro, Stefany
and I have been vibing.
You're the only one
causing a problem here.
I don't care about your thing!
Ryan, you are
so disrespectful.
You channeled this.
You're a liar and that's bull.
You're 45, you are
too old to be doing this.
Okay, no. I am too old
to be dealing with this.
I'm over it. I just know
what works for me.
And Stefany doesn't
work for me.
[upbeat music playing]
[Kelle] Jimmy. Jimmy.
You look like Michael Phelps.
[Kelle laughing]
- Cheers.
Drink it! Drink it! Drink it!
That's good.
[Jose] So, you're cool, bro?
Anything new?
[Kelle] I feel like you guys
are fighting over Stef.
I feel like, no, we're not.
[Kelle laughs]
Last night was kind of, a lot.
This like, love triangle thing
going on with Stefany.
[April] There was plenty
of volcanoes,
like, exploding.
Like, everywhere.
[Ryan S] I think
I'm going to, you know,
make sure to take
my time, figure out
who's interested in who.
Like, what are the established
relationships here.
I don't want to step
on anybody's toes.
I want to figure out, okay,
who's fair game here,
you know?
[Billy] I was like, what?
That's the highlight
of my trip.
Having a little...
He's more so, just jealous.
[Gabriel] I don't know.
I don't like making
enemies though.
That kind of doesn't
sit right with me.
[Billy] Making
enemies is fine.
After last night,
final straw, I mean.
Stefany's definitely
over Ryan, like,
I think it was a little...
I think
he embarrassed himself.
Now, I got a mature,
put together woman.
I'm excited to see
this friendship
blossoming into
something more.
I'm like, "Victory, baby."
Every time I asked her,
that we're going to spend
more time together.
- We're going to pursue
anything with each other,
- [Kelle] Oh!
did you let that
be known to him?
That's the issue.
Every time I asked
her that question,
it's never a straight answer.
I definitely think that
we're at the end of the road
with Stefany.
Stefany could care
less about Ryan's feelings.
- You know, "Woe is me.
- Right.
I'm just over here being
friends with everyone."
- No, you're not, Polly Ann.
I know you're not.
- Right.
[Ryan] This is more about
principle to me than anything.
Lying is big to me.
Can't do it.
It's triggering.
It's like, check the box
and move on.
- And that's where he's at.
- Pretty much.
But I understand that
we're here to date,
and that's kind of, sort of
what I'm re-emphasizing.
I go on a date
with his mom, right?
- Pola on a date.
- [Kelle] Yeah.
- We had a great conversation.
There was chemistry there.
You like the Latin mummies.
[Ryan] I don't know.
Mas que para tu.
Mas que para tu now.
I, a hundred percent know
who I'm going next.
I came, I saw, I conquered.
There's something that
me and Jose always say.
When you see someone
that is maybe sad
or he's not smiling,
or for any reason,
he's not having a good day.
If you smile at him,
I'm sure that person is going
to smile back to you.
- Of course!
- And that is a good
change for him that day.
[Pola] Ryan.
What are you all
doing over here?
She's waiting for you
to... Moscow?
- Is it Moscow time?
- Yes!
[Ryan] Now that it's a wrap
on Stefany,
pretty much,
there's always been
a spark between me and Pola.
You know, there have been
times when she's been
a little bit closed off.
More than I would
like for her to be.
But I do think that if I,
you know, slow down a bit,
put in some time and energy,
and effort into
getting to know Pola,
a little better,
I think that there may
be something there,
something special.
[Pola] So, my heart really
hurts for Ryan right now.
What I really feel is that
Stefany is playing
a lot of games.
But I'm relieved that
he's out of there
because Ryan is one
of my favorite.
I do miss him.
The thing is that,
he wanted to go very fast.
And he wanted to kiss me.
I was not ready for that.
But I'm sure he realized that.
And maybe we can start things
again, me and him.
No, it's probably more
than friendship.
But with his mom...
I want to make sure
she's not listening.
[Kelle] I think he's more
guarded because she's here.
Billy's great
but he's definitely
not my number one.
Jose's always been
my number one.
But Billy shows me a lot
of attention.
And Jose is like,
laissez-faire.
Like, he's just like,
chatting with everybody.
I don't really know
where his head's at.
But if Jose shows me that
there is an opportunity
to hang out,
I'm definitely hanging
out with him.
But you kind of threw me off
because of your secret.
- Oh, in the Well of Secrecy?
- Yeah.
So, mine was,
I had a quickie in a yacht
with a girl I just met.
[exclaiming and laughing]
[Kelle] So, your secret
to me seems like,
you have, like, a little
bit of a wild side.
[Jose] That was
a one-time thing.
Well, you don't know.
It could be a two-time thing.
[Jose] Well, yeah, sure.
- That's the Jose
I'm curious about.
- Okay.
[Jose] Every time I have a new
conversation with Kelle,
I see different things
about her that...
...maybe are igniting
that interest.
- They love it. They love it.
- Oh, you're so, so good.
[phone beeping]
[Pola] Hey, guys!
I got a text!
"Hello, men.
How good are you
with your hands?
In a two-minute blind massage,
it's time for the women
to judge that.
The winner will get
a special date night."
[all cheering]
I feel great about going
into this challenge.
I feel like I give
good massages.
- I have strong hands.
- Look at those hands.
I know all the spots where
the girls want to get
you know, massaged.
[Charlene] You've got to know
what you're doing.
I need the hands.
Manhandle me, please.
Not my son, but somebody.
[Shannan] We de-robe.
We get settled.
Nice and comfortable.
We are all blindfolded.
The boys are all blindfolded.
So, we have no idea
who's where.
So, each one of the sons
are given two minutes
to massage whoever's
in front of them.
And then, the women
will be scoring
on a scale of one to five.
Let the rubbing begin.
[Ryan S] I think
we're blindfolded,
so that there's just equal
footing between all the guys.
You don't know if you're
massaging your own mom.
I'm really concerned
that, you know,
not having my eyes is going
to make it really hard
to figure out kind of,
what's going on.
Like, there's definitely
the possibility of...
...you know,
touching x a few assets.
And I'm not going to be able
to tell until I'm there.
[Lisa] I'm very excited.
I don't care who massages me.
Just, yes.
[Lisa] Yup, yup.
That's it.
[moaning]
[Lisa] Oh, my gosh.
There is nothing hotter
than being massaged
by eight young men.
[Lisa] Oh, yeah.
Oh!
Oh, my God.
Don't stop.
[Kelle] What the hell
is going on over there?
[Lisa] Yeah. Oh.
If Lisa's getting a happy
ending and I'm not,
I'm going to be pissed.
Oh, yeah. Oh!
I feel like I'm doing good
in this challenge.
I feel like the moms
is giving me good feedback.
They're enjoying it.
[Lisa] So good.
I'm vocal when
I'm enjoying myself.
So, I would say a five.
[woman moaning] Yes!
Yes!
[Charlene] There you go.
Get in there.
I feel like chicken hands
are massaging me right now.
Come on! That's all you got?
Really? This person is a one.
[woman moaning]
[Billy] I didn't obviously
know who I was giving
a massage to.
But she gave me like,
no reaction.
Like, she was like,
dead quiet.
Um, made me feel like I wasn't
doing that great of a job.
[Kelle] I'm going
to give this guy a one.
I mean, I feel
like he's so timid,
he's never even touched
a woman before.
[Timmy] So, my technique is,
I spray down my whole
body before I start.
I like to lather up.
A lot of people
would be scared to go
for the booty and back.
So, I knew if I really
lather myself up,
and get in there like this,
and come back and forth
like I'm rowing a ship.
And then, come back and pull
all that energy through,
it's like, a carpet ride.
You know, I'm Aladdin on it
and they're the carpet.
I found my new roommate.
Oh, yeah.
[Soyoung] I've been
massaging Jimmy
ever since he was young.
When he get up in the morning,
I massage his feet, his legs.
[Jimmy] So, touch
is my love language.
And I learned that
from a young age.
[Kelle] Oh, yeah.
What if this is Joey?
[Kelle] This is definitely
a five.
This guy's a winner. I would
love to go on a date,
whoever this is.
[woman moaning]
That's it. Right there, baby.
Oh, yeah.
[moans]
[Gabriel] Right now, I think
I'm massaging my mom's back.
It is a little uncomfortable.
[April moans]
Baby!
[Gabriel] I was like, damn.
I kind of want to throw up
a little bit.
This guy knows
what he's doing.
This person's definitely
getting a five.
I hope it's Joey.
That was a work-out.
I started sweating.
[Charlene] I've got
to tell you guys,
you could tell a lot
about a massage.
Just saying!
And I'm so glad I had no idea
about you or anything.
[phone vibrating]
We have a winner, guys.
[all cheering]
Congratulations to...
[dramatic music playing]
[moans] Love it. Yes.
[Joey] I just think April
would be my girl.
Even though I'm young,
she says I have more
of an old soul.
I'll be around
for the rest of your life.
[Gabriel laughing]
[Kelle] Billy is more
concerned about
what his mom thinks.
But I'm not letting
anyone stop me.
We have a winner.
Congratulations to...
- Jimmy!
- [all cheering]
[Jimmy] I knew
I had this in the bag
because in my past,
I've given out more massages
than I can really count
on these hands.
But it's not the only thing
I'm probably good with.
[Stefany] You get to pick
one of the women
for a special date tonight.
I really want to take
a special woman out tonight.
I haven't gone on a date
with her yet.
And I'm really looking
forward to Charlene.
- Oh!
- [all cheering]
[Charlene] Yeah, I'm really
excited Jimmy picked me.
I didn't really have success
with Jose but I'm excited.
I think they're going
to have a really good time.
More massage, please.
But I don't want it
to escalate and lead
to a better time.
Oh, well, gee, thanks.
That's really reassuring.
Oh!
[Charlene squealing]
[Jimmy] I asked Charlene out
after winning this challenge
because I think
she's beautiful, one.
Two, I think
she is very funny.
And three, I think she's like,
open to finding love.
Nice!
[Harrison] I want her
back by 10:00 o'clock.
[all laughing]
- [Charlene] Aw, Harrison.
- [Timmy] We'll bring
you leftovers.
Open the door for her,
you know what I mean.
[Timmy] Pull the chair,
- open the door.
- [Harrison] Pull the chair.
Button the bra,
unbutton the bra.
[boys exclaiming]
I've never unbuttoned
a bra blindfolded.
[laughing and exclaiming]
This sounds really juicy.
[Jose] Congratulations,
Jimmy and Charlene.
- Jimmy and Charlene!
- [cheering]
Oh, of course.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, it is.
[Ryan S] First baby
in the family.
Oh yeah, that.
- That baby is going
to be so spoilt.
- Yeah.
[Pola] That's fine,
and that's great.
[Ryan S] I'm kind
of disappointed
when I didn't win this
massage challenge.
Would have been nice
to get the opportunity
to take Pola out on a date.
She seems so down
to earth and sweet.
A little different from a lot
of the rest of the ladies.
Maybe someone I want
to get to know better.
See if we have attraction.
[Ryan S] I already started
putting some money into
a college fund for her.
- Really?
- Oh, yeah.
Oh, that's amazing to hear.
That's like, the first
Christmas gift, basically.
It was like, okay,
I'll send you like, a doll
because you'll have that
and you'll have that forever,
- but, you know,
I'm good for the money.
- Wow!
- That's super nice to hear.
- Yup.
[Pola] Family is
the most valuable thing
that a human being can have.
I think Ryan is like,
a family guy, too.
And it's something
that attracts me.
[Ryan S] I mean, I just want
to see they're taken care of.
And like, you know,
get an education.
The most important part
of a human being
is to be well educated.
So, if you can help with that,
That's amazing, for you
to think about that.
Thank you.
What is this? Wine?
- [Ryan S] Rose, yeah.
- Yeah, the rose.
I like a sweet wine.
You do? I don't.
- No?
- No, I like Moscato.
- I drink Moscato.
A lot of Moscato.
- I like Moscato.
[both laughing]
Glass of wine, tequila.
I like to drink
a little bit, yeah.
Um...
[laughs]
[Ryan] I think Ryan's
very mature.
Very polished.
Very intelligent.
Those are qualities that
attract a lot of older women.
That could potentially
be a problem.
But I have a lot of confidence
in myself.
And the impression
that I'm making on Pola.
Hey. Nice jacket, bro.
[Pola] Yeah, you look cool.
Yeah? I love it.
Do I need to change?
[Pola] Okay, so,
stay like that.
- Should I just--
- You look very nice.
[Ryan] How would
you prefer me?
Just the way you are.
Just the way I am?
That is such
a nice thing to say.
[Pola] Just the way you are,
and the way your mom is.
It seems like all the women
that I'm interested in
already have made
some connection.
At the rate that
things are going,
I think I'm going to need
to put myself out there.
It would be great
to find love here
and I'm not giving up yet.
[Ryan] Hand hug, you forgot.
No, no, no, no, no.
Opposite, opposite.
Because you hug
with the other, loop.
I have never met somebody that
high-fives as much as Pola.
[chuckles]
That's just her thing.
That's her niche.
I think it's cute.
It's playful.
So, you know, I like it.
I'll see you.
[Pola] I'm going
to go outside.
[Harrison] Wow,
you look great.
- Thank you.
- Turn to your right.
So, I'm super excited
about my date.
I know. He's a good guy.
Yeah. He's intelligent, too.
He's just intelligent.
[Harrison] All right,
well, I love you.
Have fun.
Blessings, then.
[Harrison] I'm pretty excited
Jimmy's taking my mom out.
It was easy for me to...
you know, let my mom go out
on this date with him.
[Charlene] I feel good
for him too,
that he's finally getting
to see me possibly make
a connection.
Oh, look, and here's
my date now.
- You look nice.
- [Gabriel] You look
so beautiful.
- [Charlene] Thank you.
- Aw!
[Jimmy] I'm excited to spend
one-on-one time with Charlene.
I think Charlene's
a great pick.
I think she's a great person.
[Soyoung] I know Jimmy's
going to take care,
anybody that he dates.
[Charlene] Oh!
Look at this.
We have hors d'oeuvres.
Yeah, you look beautiful.
- So happy to be here with you.
- Thank you. Me, too.
- Well, cheers.
- Cheers.
To a beautiful night
with a beautiful person.
- Same.
- Yeah.
- Salut.
You want to know why
I thought I wanted to take
you out on a date?
- Why?
- Because...
I think you're so interesting
and have so much to say.
- You are so passionate about
everything you talk about.
- Wow.
He's saying
such really empowering,
beautiful things to me.
I'm allowing him to know
that I'm feeling him
in that moment.
I would ask, like,
from your example,
like, what turned you
on about women?
Um, let's see. What turns
me on the most...
I would say...
is when...
[Jimmy] I'm going to be real.
I'm a little nervous
because Charlene's a little
bit, you know, aggressive.
Out of all the women
in my life,
I've quite never met
a woman like Charlene.
When you kiss someone,
you can totally tell
if you have a connection.
You know, this is a perfect
opportunity for us.
- You know, for me--
- It really is.
Worth. Yeah, this is great.
This is great.
I appreciate you so much.
I know.
[Jimmy] I think that she's...
She just does it
on a different level.
She just will grab you
and just tell you exactly,
in your face, what she wants.
It's just, I've never
experienced something
like this.
Maybe like, after we eat,
we could do something
to really relax.
I think, like,
I'd like to, you know,
talk more. Like, I was
sitting here thinking like,
we should move this table.
- And you should
serve me some of these--
- Just need to fold one side.
Right, but, um,
- yeah.
- Yeah.
[Timmy] Charlene's sexual
tension energy is just
through the roof.
She's a woman that's
very passionate about
what she wants.
But it kind of makes
me want to run away.
For me, kissing is...
just as wild to me.
Like, sometimes, I'll have sex
and not kiss the person.
- Yeah, swear to God.
- Um, wow.
[Charlene] I feel like,
with Jimmy,
the lines of energy are off.
You know? There's
no alignment there.
And I just feel like
I'm shooting missiles
in the wind.
I could have probably
learned a little bit more
about Charlene
but I'm just really,
not really feeling it
as much as I thought I might.
So, I'm just going back
to the drawing board.
I told Jose that
I really liked you.
That means a lot.
[Pola] I'm really starting
to have feelings for Ryan.
I can feel his energy
through my skin.
[Joey] So, it says,
Kelle and Billy,
you are going glamping
on a secluded beach.
[all cheering]
Keep your hands to yourself.
[Jose] Kelle's not going
to have the same fun
as if I were there.
Hmm, I don't know.
[Kelle] I'm so excited.
I really can get
down and dirty.
Yeah!
[conversations overlapping]
[Joey] Would you like to go
on a little something,
something down by the water?
[April] Uh-huh. A little date.
Possibly, we could say--
I'm flattered.
- Let's go now.
- Okay.
It's a beautiful day
with a beautiful woman.
Thank you, Joey.
[Joey] Since day one,
me and April just have
that chemistry and bond.
And I decided it would
be a good idea
get even more closer
with April.
Nothing can get any better.
The lower arms.
[April] And right
here too, babe.
Right here.
[Joey] A little massage
along with it.
Uh, love it. Yes.
Very nice.
[Ryan] Wow, your skin
is beautiful, April.
- Thank you.
- Beautiful.
[April] Joey is growing on me.
Because I'm very
silly by nature.
I'm like a little kid
who just likes to have fun.
And he makes me laugh.
[April] So, how does it feel
to date an older woman?
It feels, honestly,
it's a completely
new experience
but I'm really digging it.
I'm really digging it.
And I wouldn't ask
for any other woman,
other than you,
to be on a date with.
Am I blushing?
[laughs]
You know, I first met you,
and the way you talked
and your mannerisms
and everything
are very unique.
You just like, surprise me,
and I was like...
Now, I'm blushing. Oh, my God!
You can't be hitting
me like that, April.
[April] It's kind of hard
to believe that
out of all the young
men in the house,
I am sort of gravitating
to the youngest guy.
But...
...there was so much
more to Joey
than what meets the eye.
He's got a real calmness
in his soul.
And it's kind of what
I need right now.
I'm just...
starting to remove
sort of those, you know,
those barriers
and those like, limits.
Where, "April,
you're this age.
You should be looking
at people like max,
ten years younger,
and maybe a little bit older
because I'm very young.
- even though--
- Well, yeah.
You're like 25-years-old,
aren't you?
- [Joey laughs]
- See?
[April] I'll keep him around.
- No, so--
- I'll be around
for the rest of your life.
[Joey] Don't you worry.
The rest of your life.
Aw, I promise
I'll always stay...
...sexy, like your mom.
[Joey] What gets me
going about April is,
how great of a listener
she is.
And how open she is to
everything that I have to say.
Even though I'm young,
she says that I have
more of an old soul.
Like, that really made me
happy when she said that.
She knows me the best,
out of everyone.
I just think April
would be my girl.
Watch out, watch out,
watch out, watch out.
There's a spider,
spider, spider [bleep]
I hate spiders.
Yes, yes, yes, there.
Just shake it off.
[screams] Don't leave
my side, April, please.
- No, please.
- [April] We're going.
[Ryan] Pola's a special lady.
She's top of the line.
I think a special woman
deserves a special date.
So, that's exactly what
I'm making happen
for Pola tonight.
After the drama with Stef,
Pola looks like she's
opening the door
up again for maybe
there to be an "Us."
I hope so.
I'm coming through,
step into the batter's box,
because I'm going to knock
it out of the park.
- [Ryan] Wow.
- Wow.
[Ryan] Look at you.
You look amazing, wow.
I love that.
I picked this for you.
I'm really happy that Ryan
asked me out.
I was thinking about
Ryan T all the time.
I feel really, really
attracted to him.
He makes me feel really
secure about myself.
But the new Ryan,
I really like him.
And I like to be around him.
So, I feel a little
bit conflicted.
I'm going to go out
with Ryan again,
and see how I feel about him.
I'm so excited.
You got the good view, eh?
[laughs] I do.
No, but you, too.
Well, no.
- No?
- No.
You got me.
Now, clear my view.
The best view in the house.
The best view.
[Ryan] Pola is
incredibly attractive.
But aside from that,
I can feel the positiveness
in her spirit.
Pola's very good at keeping
me actively engaged.
And that's dope to me.
That's the law of attraction.
I always have a lot
of fun with you.
I actually, I do.
- [Ryan] I always have
a good time with you.
- I do, I do.
[Pola] I told Jose
that I really liked you.
But when I met your mom,
I liked you even more.
- That means a lot.
- No, but it's the truth.
It's really important
to see who raised you.
- Where you come from.
- [Pola] Yeah.
You need to know your roots.
That's true.
Now, tell me about
your last relationship.
Very. very passionate.
- [Pola] Really?
- Yeah.
So, I'm a passionate
person myself.
So, I always tend to attract
people that are very,
very passionate.
I think that's why
we're together.
- Right?
- Lot of passion.
- [Pola] Yeah.
- A lot of passion.
- So, I like--
- I can see that.
Because every time
I'm close to you,
- Okay.
- you're looking at me.
And if I turn myself
and just watch you,
you will like,
you just turn away.
But that's something
spicy, right?
Yeah, I'm passionate, too.
So, I dated this guy.
He wanted to see me everyday.
- Right.
- And for me, it wasn't easy
because I was working,
I was with my family.
- Right.
- [Pola] He...
started to ask so much
time from me.
- Too demanding.
- [Pola] Yeah, too demanding.
You don't need
to complicate it.
- It gets complicated
by itself.
- Right.
- So, just--
- Ain't that the truth?
That's the truth.
I'm seeing a lot
of progress being made.
I think Pola's feeling
a lot more comfortable,
opening up to me.
For the first time, she's gone
into her past relationships
with me.
And kind of, sort of
opened her life up a bit.
So, I think we are in a very
good place right now.
I think our bond and our
connection has deepened.
[Pola] Can you read
what it says there?
[Ryan] Vive... el...
- [Pola] sueno.
- [Ryan] ...sonyo.
[Pola] That means,
you should live your dreams.
[Pola] The restaurant
is beautiful.
The sunset is amazing.
And just me being
by Ryan's side,
feels really good.
When I'm around anybody else,
I have to think about
what I need to say.
But with him, everything like,
just goes through with me.
[Pola] I'm really happy
to be with you.
I'm living my sueno.
And tomorrow, if you look
at me and I look at you,
don't turn around, okay?
[both laughing]
- [Pola] Salut.
- Salut.
To another exciting
day tomorrow.
I'm excited.
- To an incredible second
date with you.
- [Pola] Yes.
[Pola] I'm really starting
to have feelings for Ryan.
I can feel his energy
through my skin.
I haven't felt this way
for a long time.
[Pola] I'm really happy that
I'm sharing this with you.
And I believe, since day one,
I saw you, I said,
"This is the guy."
- Salut to life.
- [Pola] Life. Yes.
- And the adventure.
I think Billy
and your mom's going
to go for it.
Billy will be like,
uh, huh, huh, oh.
[overlapping conversations]
[phone vibrating]
I got a text!
Bring it in! Bring it in!
Come here, come here.
[Joey] So, it says,
"Hi, everyone.
For some of you,
it's time to get away
and sleep under the stars.
Kelle and Billy,
and Stefany and Gabriel,
you are going glamping
on a secluded beach."
[all cheering]
I am so glad that I get
to spend time with Gabriel.
And definitely,
out of the house.
The only thing,
is that I'm worried
about Kelle and Billy
having an overnight.
[Kelle] I'm so excited.
I feel I'm a little bit
glamorous, of course,
but I also can get
down and dirty.
Kind of like,
Sex on the Beach.
Hey Billy, you better
watch it on the beach.
Keep your hands to yourself.
For sure, always.
[Jose] Glamping is super cool.
And I'm sure they're going
to have a lot of fun.
But Kelle's not going
to have the same fun
as if I were there.
Hmm, I don't know.
Yay!
"For the rest of you,
the villa's your playground."
- My home.
- Right on.
[Kelle] What is this?
I'm so excited.
- [Billy] Yeah.
- This is so nice.
[Kelle] The tent that
we're about to stay in,
is so magical, so beautiful.
But I don't know if Billy's
mom will let us share a bed.
[Gabriel] Should we open
some champagne?
No, I'm okay.
[women squealing]
- Wow!
- Oh!
Crazy!
[Gabriel] This is a much
needed break.
Especially, after all
the fights with Ryan.
I'm here to not think
about the villa.
So, I'm just going
to decompress
and have a great time
with Stefany.
This has potential
to go past the sky.
And I'm hyped about it.
[Stefany] You got it
all over him.
- [Kelle] Wait, down there--
- [Stefany] Wait, is there--
- [Gabriel] He's soaked.
- [Stefany] He's soaked.
[Gabriel laughing]
[Kelle] I'm sorry, Billy.
Is he making you mad?
Oh, my goodness.
I can't watch.
[Gabriel] He's like, "Harder."
[Billy] Kelle doesn't
really mind PDA.
But with my mom being around,
it's a little weird.
Yeah, I definitely, am not
enjoying this one bit.
I think she could tone
it down a little bit.
You know, or I'm going
to have to maybe intervene.
I don't know, I'm not sure.
Maybe I won't.
I'll just let him
figure it out.
Maybe you could just
tell her to tone it down.
Can I tell your mom
what you were like,
going to do the other night?
No, really, should I tell her?
[Stefany] No, don't tell me.
- I don't want to hear it.
- [Billy] I plead the fifth.
[Kelle] Plead the fifth?
[Kelle] I think Billy
is more concerned about
what his mom thinks.
But I'm still going
to enjoy the moment,
and the experience.
I'm not letting
anyone stop me.
Didn't you guys need a little
alone time and stuff?
Just to get out of the villa--
[Kelle] Well, we're trying
to get away from her
but she just keeps following
us everywhere we go.
[Stefany laughs]
[both chuckle]
- [Kelle] You want to go?
- [Billy] Sure.
[Gabriel] Bye, guys.
[Stefany] Kelle's had
a few drinks.
She's, you know,
a little wild one.
[both laughing]
[Joey] So, with glamping,
what do you think about
Gabriel and Stefany?
Do you think they'll be going
at it or what do you think?
I think Gabriel's a gentleman,
and he's going to really
try to just talk and build on,
- they have that
natural chemistry.
- I think so, too.
Like you said,
there's this chemistry.
We've all seen it.
And at one point, you have
to kind of, figure out
you know, is it on a sexual,
romantic level.
- Right.
- [Lisa] And this is
the perfect opportunity
for them to find out.
[Lisa] Gabriel and Stefany,
they already have
this connection.
You know? And Stefany
and I would talk and whatnot,
and she's like,
"No, we're friends.
We're totally just friends."
And I was like,
"That's how it all begins.
Just friendship. Right?"
[Soyoung] Okay, so I think,
Billy and your mom's
going to go for it.
Exactly what I was thinking.
That's exactly what
I was thinking.
If he doesn't want
to make the move,
then she'll make
the move for him.
And if he doesn't
enjoy it, which,
that's not a possibility,
I already know
he's going to be enjoying it.
[all laughing]
[Kelle] I said,
take it off, Billy!
[Gabriel] So, now
that we're alone,
I did want to talk to you
about something.
You know, maybe if it was
any other situation,
I was dating and stuff,
I would have jumped
in and like,
started making out with you
and stuff like that.
And I just want you
to know that,
I genuinely love
getting to know you.
And I want you to know
that I really have a lot
of respect for you.
And you know, I'm just excited
to continue getting
to know you.
Oh.
[Gabriel] I've never really
had a serious relationship.
Usually, I'm very fast.
But I really am just
trying to learn
and take things slow
for once in my life.
Thank you, Gabriel.
[laughs] You're so awesome.
I love the fact that Gabriel
respects my boundaries.
It just makes me
more attracted to him.
I think after what
I've been through
with Ryan, with just one kiss,
I don't want to ruin
what I have with Gabriel
and I definitely want
to take it really slow.
- We're out.
All right, let's go.
Help me up, little princess.
My little goth princess.
[Stefany laughs] I know.
[Billy] I don't think
I can stay here.
I don't really like
the comforter of this bed.
- [Kelle] Really?
- Yeah.
[Kelle] I didn't even
think about that.
I'm thinking about
like, the vibes.
- Not the comforter.
- [Billy] Huh?
[Billy] She definitely knows
what she wants.
But I just found
it a little bit weird
to fall asleep next to someone
that was that sauced.
[Billy] Yeah.
You're going to stay?
Listen, bro.
You like, say one thing
and then, your actions
say something else.
I just don't have time
to play games.
But if you want to go
sleep with your mom,
enjoy.
I have a plan for tonight.
But we will have to sneak out.
I wanted to make her feel
how a real man should
take care of a woman.
We're in this
mission impossible
to sneak out of the villa.
Tonight, I'm going to show him
that I'm the one
he should be with.
[Kelle] Billy walked out
on me last night.
And I was so annoyed,
I couldn't even go to sleep.
Immediately went back
to the villa.
And...
...that's kind of how
that went down.
- [knocking at door]
- Oh, someone's at the door.
Don't worry, I'm up.
- [Joey] Hello?
- How are you all?
What's up, guys?
[Joey] Hey.
Is your mom sleeping?
Would it matter if I was?
- [Billy laughs]
- Because you'd wake me up.
[Joey] I'll leave you guys.
[Joey] Billy really messed up
with my mom because...
...my mom is a very
direct person.
And if you're not going
to tell her straight up,
then she's going
to blow a fuse.
[Billy] I just feel like,
moving forward,
I think I...
think we should just like,
slow things down a little bit.
I don't know how much
slower you can be,
when someone's sleeping.
Nothing was progressing
and you know that.
I'm used to dating or hanging
out with super direct men,
that know what they want.
They think it's a privilege
to spend time with me.
And I feel like
you're missing that.
[Billy] Leading up to
the glamping experience,
my feelings with Kelle
have been genuine.
I believe that we were
making a great connection.
Me leaving the glamping site
has kind of ruined that.
I do regret, kind of,
how it all went down.
Okay.
Well,
have a good morning.
- Okay.
- I'll talk to you later.
- Good bye hug.
- [Kelle] Bye, boo.
He's going to get
so much space,
he's not even going to know
that we're in the same house.
- Will you get Joey?
- Yeah.
I may have [bleep] up.
[upbeat music playing]
- [Jose] Hi!
- Yo, what's up?
- How are you, Ms. Glamping?
- Starving.
I see you, I get you.
[Kelle] Oh, I love that.
Oh, thank you.
Girl, good morning.
Hey, sorry guys.
No glam today.
You're always glamorous.
[Ryan] You look glam everyday.
We like you natural.
Thank you, babe.
Where were you last night?
I didn't see you.
Oh, I came home. Don't worry.
[Pola] And Jose was with me.
- Where were you?
- Jose should have
been with me.
He would have seen.
I was worried.
[Kelle] Billy walked out
on me last night. Douchebag.
Would you have left?
Nah, no way.
We were in agreement that
nothing's going to happen
and be respectful...
- Right, right, right.
- ...and just chat.
Especially, you've been having
that type of connection
and those vibes,
that you can chat and stay
there, you know?
Yeah.
I came here to date
young guys.
I knew why I came here.
Kelle, you get spicy
quick, don't you?
[Kelle] Yeah, I can.
No, it's not spicy.
She gets real. She's real.
- [Jose] That's awesome.
- I'm just talking my realness.
The thing about Kelle
is that I've seen her...
Nice side?
Nice side, but also,
a vulnerable side.
And that's something that
I like about someone.
[Pola] I don't feel Kelle
is right for Jose.
- Move forward.
- I am.
I am moving forward.
I have men that
literally meet me
and tell me they're in love
with me, from the beginning.
- For sure.
- [Ryan] Right.
And it's like,
you want to go slow?
Bye.
After I saw how
Kelle's date with Billy went,
I wanted to make her feel how
a real man should take
care of a woman.
She has no idea
what's about to happen.
[Kelle] Come in.
- [Jose] Hi.
- [Kelle] Hi.
- [Jose] Are you doing good?
- [Kelle] Yeah.
Awesome.
I wanted to tell you,
well, ask you,
we haven't had enough
time to be alone
and actually, properly,
have a conversation.
Have some alone time, so,
I was thinking and planning,
if you want,
I have a plan for tonight.
But we would
have to sneak out.
[laughs]
- Yeah, I'm down.
- Yeah?
Yeah. It'll be funny.
I think it would be awesome.
And not have,
- either Joey or my mom
or anyone--
- [Kelle laughs]
[Kelle] I'm super shocked.
He's asking me if I want to go
sneak out with him tonight.
So, I'm like,
"Duh, of course I do."
- Yeah, you down?
- Yeah.
Okay, let's do it.
[Kelle] Now that Billy's
out of the picture,
I am all about Jose.
Prince Charming's here.
We're both nervous.
We're both feeling
an adrenaline rush.
We're in this mission
impossible to sneak
out of the villa.
[Joey] My mom's free.
I mean, Soyoung's free.
But your eyes really
light up though,
when you talk about April.
- See? Look, right now.
- Yeah.
- [Shannan] Look at him.
- April's my girl.
- [Joey] I love talking
to her all the time.
- [Shannan] See?
Hey! Yeah.
[all chatting]
[Kelle] We're about
to leave the house.
And then, Shannan
looks straight at me.
And I try and dodge her.
I'm like, "Seriously, dude?"
I know that Jose has been
dating a lot of women
in the house.
But tonight,
I'm going to show him that
I'm the one he should be with.
[Shannan] Did you guys
see this?
[Kelle] I'm super nervous.
And I'm sure
the other women here
are going to lose
their [bleep] man.
[Pola] So, Jose
is not in my room.
I have no idea why.
He never does that.
I have no idea
what's going on.
[Kelle] Everything about Jose
is amazing. Everything.
The fact that Jose is really
stepping up right now
is huge for me.
Like, he's always been
my number one.
[Jose] When I've decided on
something, I just go for it.
[Shannan] I saw him
sneak out with Kelle.
Are you serious?
I have no words.
I am devastated.
I don't see him with her.
Tomorrow, it will be the time
to choose your match.
If your choice is a mismatch,
you could go home.
[all exclaiming]
[Ryan] That's a lot
of pressure,
I think, on a lot of people
in the house.
Ah!
That is a little bit scary.