That dream felt so real.
[Diego] Oh, wow.
It wasn't a dream, Pedro. Get up.
[distant bellowing]
[Diego] Come over.
[dinosaurs squawking]
[Pedro panting, gasps]
Wow!
First, it was a cave and now this.
Incredible.
It's just like The Verne Dimension.
No. It's better.
[squawking continues]
[Diego] Wow. This is incredible.
[Violeta] Diego, how are we going to
find Grandma here?
[Diego] It can't find the magnetic north.
[Pedro] That's odd.
And there's no sun to help orient us.
-Can't we just go back?
-[barking]
[Violeta, echoing] Soup!
[Laura] Violeta!
Violeta, come back.
[Violeta] Soup, slow down.
[Laura] Come back!
[Diego] What are you doing?
[Pompilio] I can already smell
the precious tungsten stones
in this dimension.
[echoing] I'm going to be a millionnaire.
[dinosaurs squawking]
My ancestor, Gaspard Nadar,
would be so proud of me.
See if you can find the twin volcanoes.
-[Claudio moans]
-According to Nadar's journal,
-they should be close.
-Uh-oh. [mechanical whirring]
We-- We're being watched, Pompilio.
-What? Who? Where?
-Ah! Ow. Ah.
Stop moving, Pompilio.
I can't focus if you don't stop.
-Just some bushes and rocks.
-[groans]
You are hallucinating.
[Claudio] Somebody's watching.
Ugh, it's hot. Are we there yet? [mumbles]
[mechanical noises]
[Soup barks]
Are you sure Soup is taking us to Pola?
Well, he seems pretty sure of himself.
Soup, wait! I can't walk as fast as you.
-[Diego] Let's keep moving.
-[pants]
Pedro. Pedro, what's wrong?
[breathes heavily]
It's difficult to breathe.
Yeah, it's hard for me too.
[device beeping]
The oximeter on my Clack's
indicating low pressure, but--
But what? [sighs]
It's as if we're 4,000 meters
above sea level.
[beeping continues]
But it's also indicating that we're
1,000 meters below sea level.
[exhales sharply] That makes no sense.
I'm gonna take another reading over there.
Try to catch your breath.
[Violeta] Be careful, big brother.
[Ana wheezes]
[sighs]
-[exhales sharply]
-[heavy footsteps approaching]
[Diego] Ru-- Run! [pants]
[panting]
[dinosaur squawks]
[distant bang]
I have no clue what's happening,
but I have trouble breathing.
Ah! Put me down. Let me take a look.
[in French] Oui, oui, oui.
[in English] Gently.
Come on. Parrot on board.
[Claudio] I'm like a porcelain doll.
-[Pompilio moans]
-All right. Hmm.
All right. Let me take a look.
-[exhales sharply]
-[Claudio] Mmm. [grunts]
-All right. Give me your finger.
-Huh?
So that I can measure your oxygen levels.
-[in French] Oui, oui, oui, oui, oui.
-[Claudio moans]
We need to update this system, yeah?
Something about this doesn't seem right.
You're at 81%.
I'm surprised you held on for so long.
There's barely any oxygen
in this dimension.
And you're telling me now?
Do you want to kill me?
How can you say that?
After everything I do for you.
Do you know what you and I are like?
We're like Geppetto and Pinocchio. Yeah.
Here, take my mask.
[screams]
[giggling] Kidding!
-Inhale.
-[inhales deeply]
-Exhale.
-[exhales]
-Good job, Pompi.
-[in French] Merci.
[in English] Uh, I'm shocked.
You were actually
able to shut up for a few seconds.
-Ah, shut up, [in French] stupide. [gasps]
-[grunts, screams]
[in English] The journal. Oh!
-[Claudio mutters]
-My journal! No!
Oh, it's right there.
Why'd you push it, stupid bird?
But you were about to hit me!
[groans] What are you waiting for?
Hmm?
I'm waiting for you to say the magic word.
Immediately! Go and fetch it.
I need to hear you say "please."
Claudio, get down there now.
No.
[groans]
[Diego pants] Stop. Stop, stop.
[breathes heavily]
I think we're safe. [coughs]
-What's that?
-[Pedro] Huh?
-Does that look like a door to you?
-[Soup barks]
-No wait, Soup!
-Violeta, wait a second.
[Ana] Soup might be guiding us.
[exhales sharply]
I have a hunch that my grandma is here.
-Uh-huh.
-Come on. [pants]
[in French] D'accord.
S'il vous plaît, hein?
[in English] See? Was that so hard?
"Please" and "thank you" are words that
open the doors to the heart.
Who are you speaking to?
[screams]
Crazy bird.
[mechanical whirring]
-[Claudio grunts]
-[gasps]
My journal! [laughs]
[Claudio moans]
Pompilio, are you afraid of
mechanical spiders too?
I already told you,
spiders don't scare me at all.
Good,
because there's a ton of them incoming.
-Uh, what?
-[Claudio mutters]
[Pompilio] Oh, boy.
-[screams]
-[Claudio laughs]
Run away!
-Hey, Pompi. Why don't we fly instead?
-[whimpering]
Yeah, we could fly if--
Oh, the jet pack! I can fly.
-Uh-huh?
-[laughs] See you later, stupid spiders.
[mechanical spluttering]
Ah, Pompi…
I think the propellers are
back at the camp. Hmm.
What? [screams]
Wait, Pompilio. [laughs]
Here I come. [laughs]
[panting]
[door creaks]
What is this place?
[heavy footsteps]
Shh, shh.
Uh, Grandma?
[all scream]
[screaming continues]
-Diego?
-Huh?
Violeta?
Grandma?
-[Violeta] Grandma!
-[gasps]
Kiddos!
[Pedro whimpers]
What are you doing here?
How'd you find this place?
-Your medallion brought us here.
-[Pola gasps]
We were afraid something happened to you.
[Pedro] Pola… [whimpers]
-…who is that?
-[Pola] Calm down.
That's Hans.
He's the guardian of this place.
[distorted] Welcome to my refuge.
-[Laura] Wow. How did you do that?
-He didn't move his mouth!
-Did you see that?
-It must be telepathy.
Something like that.
Ah, Hans, these are my grandkids:
Violeta, Diego. Their friends:
Pedro, Ana and…
Laura.
I saw them earlier.
They seemed lost and exhausted.
I wanted to give them this.
[Pola] You need to use these masks
to breathe here, okay?
In this dimension,
the decompression is really fast
and the oxygen levels vary a lot.
Yes, and that makes you very hungry.
You're able to read bellies as well?
You're a genius, you know.
Come over here and eat something.
You're going to need it.
-[horn blares]
-[Martín grunts]
Your workday started two hours ago.
Uh, yeah, but I spent all night
deep cleaning the bathrooms--
[Andrea] No excuses.
Wake up your siblings.
They didn't show up for breakfast.
[grunting]
Wake up, muchachos.
Hey.
Diego?
What are you up to now?
-What is this place, Grandma?
-[gasps, laughs] So cool!
You could say that I'm
on an archaeological mission.
Where are you going? Let me come too.
Mmm, you need to rest first.
Tomorrow I'll take you too.
Do you promise?
Mmm.
-Deal. [laughs]
-[laughs]
[Mauro] I'm sure they went
on that exclusive trip.
No, I get that, but it's weird, right?
Why would they stuff their sleeping bags
with pillows to fool us?
-I don't know, but, uh…
-I know.
…Pompilio will explain everything.
-We need to get to the activities.
-[Martín] No way.
I have to look for my siblings.
No. Pompilio will contact us
and explain what happened. Mm-hmm?
Andrea, I have to find them.
I have to go right now.
And I'm in charge of you.
-If you go, you're fired.
-But--
Do you want
your community service certificate, hmm?
[Hans] The conditions in this dimension
are draining for everyone.
You need to rest as well.
Don't worry. We will all be safe here.
Uh, tell me, Soup.
Do you like your new name? [chuckles]
-[beeping]
-[groans]
[engine dies]
[sighs]
-[beeping continues]
-[groans]
Diego! What are you doing here?
You promised you wouldn't go without me.
[exhales sharply]
Well, get in the back
and put your seat belt on.
-[Diego gasps]
-We have no time. Hurry up.
Hold on tight, Diego!
[cheers]
[laughs]
How did you discover this place?
I didn't discover it.
It was discovered many years ago
by my great-great-great-grandfather.
He was an extraordinary visionary
of his time.
-Jules Verne.
-No!
Did you say Jules Verne?
-[Pola laughs]
-Jules Verne?
-Uh-huh.
-Jules Verne. [cheering]
The one and only!
Hold on tight, sweetie.
We're about to land.
-Yes. Oh. Yes, yes, yes.
-[Pola laughs]
Oh, look, look.
-Wow.
-[laughs]
[dinosaur squawking]
I can't believe it.
[Pola cheers, laughs]
-[Diego] Whoa! [cheers]
-[cheers]
[Diego sighs]
[sighs]
-All good back there?
-Perfect.
I can't wait to tell Ana and Pedro
that this is the Verne Dimension
-and that I'm his great-great--
-No, Diego.
You mustn't say anything.
Only our family can know
about the existence of this world
and that's how it's going to stay.
But they're my closest friends.
You know,
Jules Verne had a very close friend too.
And, like you, he wanted to share
his discovery with him.
Biggest mistake he ever made.
[Pola] His best friend was Gaspard Nadar,
and he entered this dimension
with the intention to take
very, very valuable minerals
from the center of the earth.
[Jules] You'll destroy it!
Gaspard only cared about those minerals.
He never cared about the problem
he created when he took them.
Gaspard! [whimpers]
Fortunately, Verne was able to restore
the balance of the two dimensions.
He decided only him and his descendants
could know that a place
like this exists in the world.
We've spent years
searching for that portal.
That's why your parents are regularly
at the South Pole to take measurements.
That's how we found this portal.
And so why Mom and Dad?
Well, because all the members of the
Verne family are guardians of the portals.
Every time there's an imbalance,
we have to fix it.
[scoffs] So, that's why we're here.
-So, what's happening?
-An alteration in the magnetic field.
-What do we have to do?
-[rumbling]
[exhales sharply] Just follow me.
[rumbling continues]
Look, as long as you do the activities
as planned, you'll be just fine.
-Yeah, I know. Yeah.
-Okay?
I'm pretty sure she hates me.
Can you blame her?
She was crying for weeks.
Yeah, but it wasn't my fault.
Remember the beaver?
[teenagers laughing]
[teen] Oh, poor thing. [laughs]
[sighs]
It was my friends, okay?
Well, my ex-friends.
They were the one's who pranked her.
I wasn't involved.
Yes, your friends, your house, your party.
I swear, okay?
It wasn't me.
I, um…
You know, I had a crush on Andrea. Yeah.
Very much so.
You should explain this to her
and clear the air,
-especially since you now work together.
-She hates me.
And she won't even give me a chance.
Put yourself in her shoes, dude.
[objects rattle]
[rumbling]
Is that an earthquake?
It's over.
[exhales sharply]
[Pola] There it is.
Verne's machine should be located
just past these rock formations.
Don't look down. Just look forward.
The secret is to focus three feet
ahead of your next step.
[rumbling]
[pants] I'm afraid of heights.
Look at me, sweetie.
[exhales sharply] I'm a Verne.
I'm a Verne. I'm a Verne. I'm a Verne.
I'm a Verne. [grunts]
-[Pola laughs]
-[breathes heavily]
That was easy, right?
Oh, my.
[sighs, sniffs]
-Look.
-Wow.
[both laugh]
[sighs] You'll love it.
Wow.
Incredible.
Right? And this whole system of dynamos
and valves was designed and built by Verne
to maintain the earth's magnetic field.
And, according to this guide…
we have to shift these levers in order.
This is the first one.
[Diego] Um.
[Pola] Yes.
All right, now the next one. [grunts]
[Diego] And now I think it's this one.
Wait a sec.
How do I do this? Please, let me do it.
Please, let me do it.
No, no, no. I have to do this, Diego.
-Ah! Oh.
-[siren blares]
Now what are we supposed to do?
[siren continues]
What about this?
This can replace the lever.
Good idea. Come on.
[Diego grunts]
[groans] Great. [laughs]
This is the last one.
[straining] Come on. Help me.
[Diego strains]
[sighs] Now what?
-My jacket.
-Great.
Perfect.
-One, two, three.
-[Diego grunts]
-[siren stops]
Ah. [breathes heavily]
-Oh, my.
-Did we do it?
Yes. [laughs]
Time to get back to our world,
erase the memories of your friends
and get out of here as soon as possible.
We're gonna erase their memories?
Of course. So, what happened
with Nadar doesn't happen again.
Remember, Diego…
the Verne family is the only one that can
know about the existence of this place.
Do you promise
that you'll keep this secret
and be one of the guardians
of the Verne Dimension?
[Mauro] Everyone excited to focus on
fishing today?
-Yes.
-Safety is of utmost importance.
-Where is Martín Medina?
-Uh, I don't know.
Late. Again.
It might just be me,
but you seem too interested in Martín.
[Andrea sighs]
[Martín] Hey, kids,
your favorite beaver is here! [cheers]
[Andrea huffs]
What are you doing?
I'm asking for forgiveness.
So,
how do you like the beaver costume, huh?
You really have crossed the line.
Don't show your face to me again.
-That wasn't the idea.
-You're fired.
Okay, but before you go-- [grunts]
-[kids laugh]
-Andrea, why was he apologizing to you?
-Andrea!
-What are you doing?
[Ana] Where'd you go? Why didn't you wait?
I hope everything went well.
-Where were you?
-Mmm. We went out for a walk.
-[Violeta laughs]
-[sighs] Yeah, we went for a walk.
All right, time to go back home.
-No.
-No. Why?
Yes, let's go home.
[explosion, rumbling]
That was big.
Volcano.
[explosion continues]
Those are weird volcanoes.
[Pola] The volcanoes of the Apocalypse.
JOURNEY TO THE CENTER
OF THE EARTH