I, Jules Verne,
went around the world
in a hot air balloon,
traveled to the depths of the sea
and went to the center of the Earth.
Everything I wrote, I lived,
was not in our world,
but a parallel universe that I discovered.
[alarm ringing]
It was there that I developed
some of my most important inventions.
[siren wailing]
I discovered that everything that happens
in one universe affects the other.
Therefore, dear children, grandchildren,
great-grandchildren
and generations to come,
I pass on to you the duty
to guard these secret portals.
-What is happening here?
-[dog barks]
And remember,
should you need to enter the portal,
only do so
when the Earth loses its balance.
-I hope you such a day never comes.
-[siren ends]
I am leaving you detailed instructions
on how to fix an imbalance
in the other dimension,
and I must repeat
the most important thing:
do not share this secret with anyone.
-The only one I trust is you.
-"The only one I trust is you."
"My descendants
and keepers of this secret portal."
JOURNEY TO THE CENTER
OF THE EARTH
[thunderclap]
-[child 1] Where are we going?
-[child 2] Check the map.
-[thunderclap]
-[child 1 sighs]
-[device beeps]
-The GPS isn't working.
So can we go back then?
I'm dying from hunger.
[growl, roar]
Something tells me
you're not the only one.
[dragon groans]
[child 2 gasps]
[child 1] Oh.
[roars, growls]
[dragon roars]
[all panting]
[both gasp, scream]
-[dragon 1 growls]
-[child 2] Quick, run faster!
-[growls, roars]
-[all panting]
Just wait. I can't keep running.
My heart's gonna explode.
-Pedro, what are you doing?
-[Pedro] Don't worry.
Repellent.
One spray keeps the lizards away.
If it eats me, I'll taste like repellent,
and I'll be spit out.
-[dragon 1 roars]
-Pedro!
-[dragon 1 groans]
-[Pedro whimpers]
Pedro!
[dragon 1 coughs, whines]
Let's get out of here!
[dragon 1 roars]
[dragons roar, growl]
-Stop. There's a cliff.
-[Pedro] Oh, I hate cliffs.
There's no other option. We have to jump.
-Are you crazy?
-Come on. We have to do something soon.
[child 1 pants, grunts]
[both roar]
We can't hear anything
when you're screaming!
[both whine]
[both roar]
[roars]
-[all screaming]
-[dragon growls]
[screaming continues]
[older kid]
For heaven's sake, can you stop shouting?
It's impossible to be in this house
with you guys making so much noise
all the time.
It's my room, so I can do whatever I want.
-Come on, guys.
-Ugh, really?
This is the best part of the game.
-What's wrong with you?
-The Verne Dimension.
Aren't you a little too old
to be obsessed with fantasies?
Even Violeta acts more mature
than you guys.
-[Violeta barks, pants, whimpers]
-Ugh.
[Violeta sniffing, barks]
Yeah, your sister's definitely mature.
[Violeta growls]
-Cuckoo.
-[Violeta barks]
Violeta, I can't take any more.
Look, when we get to camp
tomorrow morning, do me a favor.
Just act like you don't know me at all.
You got it?
Okay.
[door closes]
Do you really like being a puppy?
Yeah! I love puppies.
But since I cannot have one--
[child 1]
Phew, Lampisben almost caught us.
There was a glaring mistake in the game.
Verne wrote about dinosaurs,
not two-headed dragons.
Well, anyway, for the next time,
we will be well-prepared.
My Clack is the perfect tool.
Check out my new additions.
[Clack beeps]
-[child 3 screams]
-[older kid] What did you break this time?
[child 1] Uh…
[crows cawing]
[microwave buzzes]
[buzzing continues]
-[thud]
-[buzzing continues]
Hmm.
[crows cawing]
[cawing continues]
-[thump]
-[crow caws]
[older kid] Grandma!
Grandma. Grandma. My idiot brother
used this thing to break a window.
-It's not a thing, it's a Clack.
-Clack?
-Just give it back.
-No, you're not getting it.
Give it back, Martín.
Your brother's an inventor too.
And you have to respect that.
Do you remember when you tried to invent
those glasses with a camera?
Yeah, but those things actually worked.
Unlike this thing
that almost killed his friends.
[Diego's grandmother] Martín.
Mmm.
[sighs] Here's your invention, you baby.
I'm not a baby! [grunts]
All right, enough. Hey, hey!
No more fighting. Stop.
I'll help you calibrate your Clack later.
Why haven't you started packing
for summer camp yet?
Camp starts tomorrow, kiddos.
Everybody has more important things to do.
My parents have their research
on the other side of the world,
you have your explorations,
Martín has his own things.
-Hmm.
-I get it.
Everything's more important than me.
[gasps]
[sighs] Go talk to him.
Diego!
[sighs]
[cawing continues]
[person grunts]
[device buzzing, beeping]
[beeping continues]
[laptop beeping]
Are you seeing that, Julia?
The Earth's magnetic field is fluctuating
rapidly, and that worries me.
I'm going to try to go in today.
If I succeed, you and Víctor
have to check the measurements
-of the magnetic field.
-You're going in today?
What are you gonna do with the kids, Mom?
You can't leave them alone.
I'm not leaving them alone, Julia.
Tomorrow they're going to the exploration
camp, and they're super excited.
They'll be safe there.
Martín will keep an eye on them.
You're right. [sighs]
Everything is going to be just fine.
-Mm-hmm.
-[beeping continues]
[Diego] I wanna go with you.
I'm a good explorer.
I'll be helpful there.
I know. But you'll be exploring at camp
with other kids.
-That doesn't count.
-[groans]
Why are you still up?
[Diego's grandmother sighs]
You're leaving us?
Mm-hmm. I am, Martín.
I'm leaving you in charge, okay?
Be sure to take care of them.
[scoffs]
[Diego's grandmother] Diego.
I promise you that we'll go together soon.
[sighs]
[panting]
[sighs] Time to go.
[breathes heavily]
-[person in French] Bonjour, madame.
-[gasps]
Qu'est-ce que c'est…
[in English] What are you doing here?
-Yeah.
-On your shoulder there's a black widow.
Whatever you say.
This piece of junk isn't a black widow.
No, your other shoulder.
-Where? [gasps, shouts]
-[laughing]
Get the spider off me!
Get it off! Get it off!
[portal whirring]
[dog barks]
[thunderclaps]
I thought you weren't afraid of spiders,
Pompilio. [laughs]
-[whirring intensifies, ends]
-[Pompilio] What's that? [pants]
Oh, no. She ran away.
No, no, no, no! I've been
trying to enter this portal for years.
It's all your fault, Pompilio.
-If you weren't afraid--
-I'm not afraid. I was merely startled.
[chuckles] Yeah.
-No, no, no, wait, Pompilio! [groans]
-Shh!
-[explosion]
-[Pompilio shouts]
[groaning]
-[in French] Mon Dieu.
-[dog barks]
-[growls]
-[in English] Wow. W-- Wow.
-Quickly, follow that dog!
Follow him, you ugly bird.
-Follow him yourself.
-But you can fly.
No, I-- I can't.
What do you mean you can't?
Fly! Go, quickly.
-Well, my battery… [distorted] …is deple--
-[in French] Oh mais c'est tu…
[in English] I know your battery
doesn't die, so go follow him, you coward!
[in French] Ça suffit.
[in English] Sign up for the best camp
in the whole world.
The biggest!
[Pompilio, on TV] The one and only
nature camp run by Pompilio Calderón.
Where you can enjoy activities such as:
Mountain hiking!
-Bonfires!
-[children cheer]
Not to mention extreme sports!
This is the one and only exploration camp
of Pompilio Calderón.
And Claudio!
Kid, what do you say?
Are you going to be there?
-You can't miss it for the world.
-[laughs]
[Claudio] Now accepting all
major credit cards.
[children]
Come to Pompilio Camp! [cheering]
Yeah!
[singsongy] I'm going to camp Pompilio.
I'm going to camp Pompilio.
-Let's go now!
-[phone ringing]
Yeah. Yeah. We'll head out soon.
-[ringing continues]
-It's Mom.
-Hi, Ma.
-[Julia] Hi, honey.
Look. Look who's here.
Hello, Vio. How are you?
I'm good, Mom! Bye, Mom!
[both laugh]
[Julia] She seems happy.
Yeah, she's doing really good.
And I am too.
Really happy going to this camp.
Martín, do it for your university, please.
Sweetie, you have to be grateful
that Mauro was able to get you a gig
for your community service requirement,
yeah?
-I know.
-[Vio] Martín!
What happened to the TV?
-[Víctor] Julia, look.
-[Julia] What is it?
Martín! The TV!
Martín, we have to deal with
an urgent matter happening at the base.
-What's happening? Is everything okay?
-Take care of your siblings.
-[beeping]
-We have to go.
-That doesn't look good.
-No.
[Julia] Ugh.
You gotta hurry, Ma.
[counselor, on PA] Welcome
to the best nature camp in the world.
Camp Pompilio. A place where nature…
-[child] It looks amazing.
-[Vio] Yay!
[Martín] Ugh. Watch it, this is a new car.
I'm gonna get there first.
-Where's Pompilio?
-No, Violeta.
Hey, wait a sec.
I just want to make it clear
that I'm not your nanny here, okay?
Hey, Diego.
You're gonna stay out of trouble, yeah?
-Yeah.
-Pompilio! Pompilio!
-[Pedro] Wait for me!
-Wow!
Unfortunately, family members
can't go past this point.
Hey. You know the deal. No cell phones
allowed. You have to leave them here.
[counselor, on PA]
Please, your leave phones…
[teen] …if you'd like to take your child--
Oh, you see, I also work
at the Calderón Foundation.
I just wanted to walk my sister in.
She's just a bit-- She has a hard time
socializing sometimes, you know?
[teen sighs] I understand.
Let me know if you need anything.
I'm here any time.
Thanks so much.
Hi. I'm Ana.
-Hi. Uh, she's--
-I'm Laura.
Uh, do you-- Um, do you want to join us?
-[Violeta] I wanna go in now!
-[Laura] Huh?
Yes.
Go. Have fun. Move. [chuckles]
[Ana] Come on.
[Violeta] I'm gonna get there first!
Hey! Laura!
Remember to stay with your group.
-[Laura] Okay.
-Yeah.
[counselor, on PA]
The different areas of the camp are marked
with numbers and letters…
-[child 1] Thanks, Richard.
-…if you need help…
-[child 2] There he is!
-[sighs]
[child 2] I got here first.
-Look, Antonio.
-Yeah?
I brought a special light
to improve the quality of our videos.
They'll be super lit now, am I right?
And I brought a boom
so that our sound quality will improve.
I don't care about your toys.
I'm about to film
my entrance into the camp.
Hey. Why are they carrying your things
and not mine?
Hmm, I don't know. Let me think.
Oh, I know. Because I'm an influencer,
Pompilio's nephew,
and last but not least, I'm Calderón.
And you? Let me guess.
Just another face in the crowd.
But here, you may have this--
I'm not just another face in the crowd.
Whatever. Yeah.
Come on. Come on. Follow me.
I have something cool to show you.
[Mauro] All right, I'm gonna time you.
Okay. Ready?
-One, two, three.
-[stopwatch beeps]
Dude, I'm so glad you're here
for your community service requirement.
-It's gonna be great.
-Trust me, I didn't have a choice.
Being a counselor
is like the nerdiest thing ever.
Hey, being counselor is supercool.
-No, it's super nerdy.
-[blows whistle]
[Martín grunts]
What are you guys doing
fooling around here?
-Pompilio's about to present.
-[Martín] Andrea?
An-- Andrea Bromo?
[stammers, chuckles] Martín Medina.
Just my luck running into you here,
of all places.
There's something different about you,
yeah?
Yes, I know, I've changed.
I'm not the Andrea that you once knew.
What are you doing up there?
You should get back to work.
Mauro was showing me the ropes.
And I just… [chuckle] …tangled.
Yeah. Sure. You're still as immature
as you always were.
Mauro, get him down, will you?
You helped him get up there
in the first place.
Get down for the presentation.
Chop, chop, chop.
-[Martín] Help me, man.
-Okay. Hold on. Just hold on.
-[groans]
-Right there. Almost. Perfect.
[Ana] This is gonna be
the best camp of our lives.
[Violeta] Yeah!
Yeah, but where is it?
It's over there!
-[Violeta] I wanna see Pompilio!
-[Diego panting]
[bird chirping]
[Antonio]
Please subscribe because we're gonna have
a ton of crazy content the next few days.
Including a zip line…
-No, my putty clay!
-…maybe even some pranks.
Wow. I didn't know the camp is
allowing preschoolers in now. [chuckles]
[Antonio's friend]
Ooh, a little preschooler.
Uh-oh. This might be troublesome.
-[Laura] Give me my putty, please.
-Leave her alone.
-Why should I?
-Give it back.
-Give the putty back to her.
-You stay out of this.
And why should I listen to you, huh?
Because you can beg your daddy
and buy your own.
[children murmur]
[Antonio grunts]
Antonio, don't fight, don't fight.
You just act tough
because you're a little older.
[laughs] Guys.
Here's a bunch of preschoolers.
[older kid] Let's go, Antonio.
Ceremony's about to start.
Do not embarrass us.
We're Calderóns.
Go. Give it back.
Saved by the bell.
But you won't be as lucky next time.
[Antonio's friend] Losers.
You guys are the real losers!
[Diego sighs]
Here.
Thank you.
[Diego] Don't stray too far.
-Let's go.
-Yeah.
Come on.
-[Violeta] Quickly.
-[Ana, Laura giggle]
-[children cheering]
-[Violeta] Yay!
[children chanting]
Pompilio! Pompilio! Pompilio!
-Thank you.
-It's an honor, sir.
I know. I know.
Go, go, go, go.
[Violeta] Yay, it's Pompilio! Yay!
[children cheer, applaud]
Are you guys ready for an adventure?
[children] Yeah!
Are you ready to have some fun?
-[children] Yeah!
-[Mauro] Yeah! [chuckles]
-Are any of you afraid?
-[children] No!
Superb!
Because here at the magnificent
nature camp of Pompilio Calderón,
you can look forward to
a month full of excitement!
-Tournaments!
-[in French] Expéditions!
-[in English] Tournaments!
-Bonfires!
-Tournaments!
-Extreme spo--
[in French] Mais ce n'est pas possible.
La répétition, ça va?
-[children laughing]
-[Pompilio] Ça va bien? Bah vas-y.
[in English] And remember…
[all laugh]
…only the bravest
will be able to come on
the most exclusive and magnifique trip.
-[child] Yeah!
-Who wants to go?
-[Violeta] Me!
-[children] Me!
-Toi!
-He's my uncle.
-Et toi!
-Wow.
Et toi aussi!
So, everybody, try your best
and listen to your counselors. Ah.
And the most important thing of all.
Ah.
The no-go zone.
Under no circumstance
can you enter this area.
And that's because this area is
super-duper dangerous.
[children murmur]
Because these lands belong to the dead,
anyone who trespasses has a terrible,
terrible curse at fate.
-[Claudio groans]
-And last, but not least,
I want to take the time to thank
our sponsors: the Calderón Foundation.
-[both] Hearts are ice cold!
-[older kid whoops]
Represented ici by my beloved nephews:
Felipe and Antonio Calderón.
A foundation dedicated to preserve the
Arctic mass melting in the north pole.
A big applause for them. S'il vous plaît.
[children applauding]
And now,
I declare the official inauguration
of the exploration camp
of Pompilio Calderón!
[laughing, cheering]
The challenge we have for you
will not be easy.
Each team will need to paint
one of these totem poles.
So prepare yourself,
because it needs to be impeccable.
-Not a drop of paint out of place.
-[child] Oh, no.
The team that finishes first
and has the best-looking totem
will win
points for the trip with Pompilio.
[children] Yeah! [cheering]
With the three of us,
this one's a piece of cake.
Ready, kiddos?
-[children] Yeah!
-[Andrea] Your time starts now.
Hey, guys,
I have a brilliant idea to help us win.
All right? Come on.
[Andrea] That's looking great.
Martín, could you keep an eye out on them?
I really need to take a--
What?
Could you keep an eye out?
-I need to go to the ladies room.
-Yeah, yeah.
-Yeah?
-[chuckles]
[engine starts]
[engine running]
Antonio, check out
what those losers are doing.
I can't lose to those preschoolers!
Oh, I have an idea.
Come here, come here. Faster.
[whispers]
The idea is the two of you will be…
I'm finally going to enter that portal.
Huh? First,
we have to find that stupid dog, Pompilio.
Are you going to humble yourself
and finally go look for that dog, Claudio?
I already told you my batteries are low.
-Besides, he went really far.
-Ugh.
Stop concocting fantasies.
You don't have to charge any batteries.
You only have one, and it lasts forever.
-Oh, are you serious?
-[Pompilio] D'accord?
-Ah, d'accord, d'accord.
-Oui, oui, oui, oui, oui, oui, oui.
[grumbles]
Gaspard Nadar.
Today is the day.
Finally, one of your descendants
will make history again.
I'll finally get the precious tungsten.
-Yes! Give me a high five. [squawks]
-[groans]
Oh, sorry.
-[Pedro gasps] Wow.
-[Diego] Wow.
You're a really good artist.
-Thank you.
-[Antonio's friend 1] That's so cool.
Get the putty!
-Run, run!
-[Pedro] What are you doing?
-Give it back. Don't touch it.
-What's your problem?
This is getting old. Just leave us alone.
[Antonio's friend 1] Aw, look
at what the preschooler made. So cute.
-[Ana] Hey, stop.
-Leave us alone.
-Give it back.
-Make me.
[Antonio's friend 2]
It's really horrible. Did you make it?
-[Ana] Seriously, stop it.
-Is that's all you losers can do?
-You shut your mouth.
-[Antonio] Hey, calm down, okay?
Give her back her sculpture. Give it back.
Give it back.
Since you did such a good job,
we wanna film it.
Maybe we'll get some more views.
[Pedro] All right,
let's put on the finishing touches.
-[engine starter whirring]
-[Ana chuckles] Oh.
-[Ana] What happened?
-I don't know. It's not working.
-[whirring continues]
-Oh, Diego. Stop playing around.
-[whirring intensifies]
-[Diego] I'm not playing around.
[Ana] Please, just make it stop.
Kids, what are you up to?
What's going on here?
-Turn off the power.
-Diego, do something. Anything.
-Diego! Diego!
-[Andrea] What are you trying to do?
-[Laura] Turn it off! Turn it off!
-[Ana grunts]
[Pedro gasps, wheezes]
Martín!
I wanna pay those jerks back so bad.
I wanna steal their toothbrushes
and deep clean their toilets with it…
[chuckles]
…and then put them back for use.
Cleaning the bathrooms sounds more like
a punishment for us, no?
Right? Wait. The fire.
We wait till the fire goes out,
then we grab the ashes
and put it in their sleeping bags.
-Hmm?
-Ah.
There's a rat!
-It's not a rat, it's my puppy.
-Is that your puppy really?
-Then tell me what's its name.
-His name is Soup.
[chuckles] Soup?
That's not a name of a puppy.
-Well, I guess it is now.
-[Soup whines]
-[Soup growls, barks]
-[gasps] Soup, come back!
No, Violeta, wait!
But-- Uh, guys. Wait, that's--
Whatever, let's go!
-[Soup barking]
-Soup!
-[Soup snorting]
-What are you doing?
[Violeta] Soup.
[Diego pants]
[Diego]
I don't think we're supposed to be here.
This is my grandma Pola's medallion.
But there could be many medallions
like this one.
No, this one is unique.
It belonged to
her great-great-grandfather.
She had it on her
when she left last night.
-So, that means that she--
-My grandma's somewhere around here.
I'm worried about her
since she lost the medallion.
-[Soup whining]
-[Diego sighs]
Guys, I need to find my grandma.
-She could be in danger.
-[Soup whining]
Can I count you in?
-[all] Yeah.
-[Violeta laughs]
Time to find her.
[Diego] Grandma Pola!
[Diego's voice echoes]
-Grandma!
-[voice echoes]
[Violeta] Grandma!
-[crow caws]
-[Pedro gasps, breathes shakily]
Stop messing around, Pedro.
This is serious.
We need to move now.
Before they find out we're not there.
Okay.
[Pedro sighs]
-That's my grandma's car!
-[Violeta gasps] She should be here then!
Grandma!
[Diego panting]
-[Pedro] Her car looks fine to me.
-[Diego] It wasn't forced open either.
I'm gonna try the black light.
-[switch clicks]
-[device beeping]
Look. Footprints. Should be my grandma's.
And they lead that way.
Hey, guys, isn't this the place
that Pompilio said is off-limits
and dangerous, extremely dangerous?
-[Soup barking]
-[Violeta] Soup!
-Soup!
-[Diego] Wait, Vio.
-[Soup barking]
-We have to keep going.
The footprints go in.
What if grandma's in danger?
Guys, we need to follow Soup.
Yeah.
This image…
What is it? I'm unable to get a clue.
[Soup barking]
[Claudio] It's the dog.
Along with some kids from the camp.
Sacrebleu. Those kids shouldn't be here.
-[Violeta] What should we do?
-[Diego] I don't know.
-[Violeta] Soup!
-[Soup whining]
[Violeta] Come.
[Soup whines]
[Violeta] Wait. Wait for me.
[Claudio gasps]
That kid has the medallion. [screeches]
[Ana] Diego?
Are you sure?
[Diego] Come on.
[Pedro] Hey, let's stop here.
It's really dark in there.
[Diego] We have to keep going
till we find my grandma.
-[rattling noise]
-Let's go.
[water dripping]
[Ana] We've come really far, Diego.
-[Soup barking]
-[Violeta] Soup!
[Diego] She's right. We came this far.
Come on.
-Grandma!
-[voice echoes]
Pola!
Come on, Laura.
[Laura grunts]
[Diego sighs]
[Violeta] Oh. The footprints end here.
[Diego groans]
-Pola!
-[voice echoes]
Pola!
Grandma, where are you?
I don't like this.
Don't you think there could be ghosts?
Mummies? Even werewolves?
-[person] Kids.
-A mummy!
[gasps]
-[Claudio laughs]
-Pardon? What did you say?
[Claudio laughs] They mistook you
for a mummy, Pompilio.
-Sorry, Pompilio. I didn't recognize you.
-[Pompilio] C'est très bien.
Why are you here, petits garçons?
This is an extremely perilous area.
Was that not clear the first time around?
Their grandma is missing.
Well, I'm known as the best explorer
in the world, you know?
If there's a person missing,
then I'll go find them.
But I'll need, uh… something of hers.
Some object,
something I can touch physically.
Do you have anything?
Her medallion!
Superb.
If grandma lost this medallion,
that means something's wrong.
May I examine it?
[robotic whirring]
S'il vous plaît?
-[electricity crackles]
-[Pompilio shouts]
-[Pompilio grunts]
-[Claudio grunts]
Hey, kid, what was that for?
It must have a thousand volts.
[Soup growling]
[Diego gasps]
-Shoo, get out of here.
-[Soup growls]
Don't worry, Pompilio's on our side.
He's our friend.
Well now, um…
I'll go look for your grandmother.
But all of you get back to camp now.
-Allez, allez!
-[Violeta] Look, a piece of cloth.
-[Diego] That's my grandma's handkerchief.
-[scoffs] That's not possible.
That wall's been there
for a thousand years.
[Diego] Look, her footprint.
My grandma must be in there. [grunts]
-[Claudio] Uh-oh. Oh, yeah, yeah.
-[Diego] Grandma! Grandma.
[Violeta] Open! [strains]
[Ana] I think this is a secret door.
[chuckles] What fanciful ideas,
mademoiselle.
Uh, it's-- it's merely a wall. A wall.
Come on, time to get back. Allez, allez.
Wait, Pompilio.
We can't take the medallion.
[Violeta grunts] Grandma!
Let them open the portal
and then we'll get rid of them.
[Claudio] Mm-hmm.
-I know what to do.
-[Claudio grunts]
We let them enter with the medallion,
then we can get rid of them later.
Oh, wow. You're--
You're a genius, Pompilio.
Oui, oui, oui. I know. I know.
[Claudio] Hey, look! Some symbols! Huh?
Oh là là. Look what we have here.
[Claudio] Huh?
[Claudio] Oh, oh.
[Diego]
It's the same symbol as the medallion.
Oh, I wonder what will happen
if we put it together.
Yeah. Maybe the the door will open.
What a brilliant idea.
How did you come up with that?
-Thanks. I saw it in a movie.
-[Pompilio] Mmm.
[portal whirring]
Come on. That must be where my grandma is.
Stop. Don't move, all right?
This could be a death trap.
This could be the gates of the Apocalypse.
-No, that's where my grandma--
-Silence, mademoiselle!
I am not about to allow you
to endanger yourselves.
Claudio and I will go search
for your grandmother.
-All of you will go back to the camp now.
-[Diego] No.
I'm going to save my grandma.
Then you leave me with no other option.
Looks like some force will be needed.
My favorite chemical agent.
It's infallible.
Claudio, show them.
[Claudio cackles, strains, farts]
[children groaning, retching, coughing]
[Ana] I can't breathe. [coughs]
[Claudio] Hey, coward, let go of me!
[screaming]
[Pompilio screaming]
[Claudio] Let go of me!
[Claudio] I don't have a passport!
Mommy! [cries]
[Laura] The portal!
It's closing up!
[Soup barking]
-[Violeta] Soup, wait for me.
-Wait, Violeta!
-[Violeta screams]
-[Diego] No!
JOURNEY TO THE CENTER
OF THE EARTH