It's about time.
Try it a little more like this.
Did you maybe push too far?
Are you questioning me?
No one else
at scene of murders,
only Omni-Man.
Put an A-6 surveillance team
on the Graysons.
I was thinking
finals are coming up,
maybe we could
go over everything together.
Works for me.
Today,
we have lost Titans.
It is my pleasure
to introduce
the new Guardians of the Globe.
We have a benefactor,
it seems.
I'd say I'll miss you, brother,
but I can always make
another one.
What are you doing
in my house?
Seeking clues.
Answers.
Debbie?
You all right?
I'm fine.
Your men are too slow.
The desert
is unforgiving, Zaeim.
Heh, not as much
as what's under it.
Move.
Out of my way!
Master...
soon, you will once again
teach this world
what it means to truly suffer.
Help me!
My God...
he's resurrecting Ka-Hor.
Gain some altitude!
You're messing up
the desert.
Huh?
Uh... sorry.
And pick up the pace.
You need to push yourself
if you want to build
speed and endurance.
I can't believe I still
have to exercise.
What, you thought being
a Viltrumite was easy?
Show off.
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa!
Okay, okay,
let's take a break.
Now you're talking.
Last one to Mount Everest
does the dishes for a week.
Go!
Yeah!
Wait... where's Mount Everest?
It's the high one!
Whoa!
Take deep breaths, buddy.
The air's thin up here.
No... kidding...
What the fuck?
Hi. Sorry.
It's okay.
I'm...
Sometimes, I forget
how beautiful
this planet can be.
Too bad the human race
is hell-bent
on destroying it.
Good thing
they got us, right?
Huh.
Yeah, I guess.
So, is Viltrum that different?
Oh, it's very different.
We've ended wars
all over the universe,
brought peace
to thousands of galaxies,
lifted alien races
out of the mud
and into the future.
It's why I'm here
on Earth.
It's why you're here.
I still can't believe
you left everything
to come help a planet
you'd never even
seen before.
I told you,
I was part of the...
...world betterment committee.
Yeah, I know,
but that's still
not a reason.
Well, when
your grandparents died,
I was lost
for a long time.
They were
the only family I had.
Coming here
felt like a chance
to build something new.
You mean,
like with Mom?
Yeah, your mom
changed everything.
She turned this place
from a job to a home.
Then you came along
and changed it all again.
Huh.
I don't know
if I could do that.
Do what?
Leave everything behind.
Hey, keeping
the universe safe,
living up to
our people's heritage,
it takes sacrifice, Mark.
That's what
I'm trying to teach you.
Sure. I get that.
Okay.
All right,
one more round, huh?
Last one home takes out
the garbage for a month...
Ha, ha, ha!
Ha...
Ah, man...
Lies!
The GDA are snakes.
They don't care about us,
or my poor Josef.
Olga...
No Olga.
I am Russian, my dear,
I know how governments work,
and yours is no different.
Cecil's searching
for the killer...
Is he?
No one is in jail.
No one is on the news.
They know who did this,
and they don't care.
Why wouldn't they care?
I don't know, but I can tell
when people are lying,
and people are lying
about this,
which is why I'm moving
back to Moscow,
to my family.
You can help me
sell my house.
Uh, yes, absolutely.
Olga...
Did Josef ever lie to you?
Of course,
all heroes do,
but I only made the mistake
of believing him once.
When he told me
everything was going
to be fine.
Boy, I am going to love
not taking out the garbage
for a month.
Yeah, yeah,
quit rubbing it in.
So, I spent all day
teaching our son
to break the sound barrier.
Turns out
the only motivation he needed
was getting ready
for a hot date.
A date? Hold up.
Tell me everything.
It's not a date.
Amber and I
are just hanging out.
Hanging out?
Wow.
Try not to sweep the girl
off her feet too much.
Guess where
they're going?
Out.
Ooh, out.
Every woman's favorite
destination
for a romantic evening.
I don't even know
what we're doing.
She planned the whole thing.
Oh, a take-charge girl.
I like that.
Are you both finished?
'Cause I have
six time zones to wash off.
What say we go out,
too, huh?
Can't let a couple
of teenagers show us up.
Olga wants me
to sell her house.
Ah, the poor woman's barely
holding it together.
She thinks there's a conspiracy
around the murders.
Ah, she needs to quit drinking.
Nolan...
What?
You remember last year's
Christmas party.
She was a wreck.
Mm...
This is, like,
all the best desserts in one.
Right?
I ate way too many of them
in the Philippines last summer.
What were you doing there?
Helping build schools.
It was one of those
group volunteer things.
Wow.
How was that?
It felt so good,
and it just made me realize
that we're in a total bubble
that keeps us from seeing
what the world's actually like.
How about you?
You done any traveling?
Uh, well...
I've been to Mount Everest.
What?
You're kidding.
No, I, uh, visited with my dad.
A father-son trip thing.
That's unbelievable.
How did you like Nepal?
Or did you go through China?
Uh...
Wow, those are cool...
boxes.
They're called "bauls."
Um, "b-a-u-l" baul.
I wanted to bring one home
from the Philippines,
but they don't exactly
fit in a backpack.
Maybe this is your lucky...
Oh, my God,
look at how cute those are.
Those are rice separators.
And so reasonably priced.
Thanks.
Just imagine all the rice
you're gonna separate now.
What exactly do you
separate it from?
Wondered if you'd come.
You were in my house.
You frightened my wife.
You murdered seven people.
Maybe it was you.
Maybe you came
to finish the job you started
with the Guardians.
You're the demon after all.
Hmm...
and demons know evil
when they see it.
If you threaten my family again
with your conspiracy theory
bullshit...
You'll kill me?
I won't have to.
Who do you think
they're gonna believe?
Me or you.
Won't give up, Nolan.
Can't hide truth.
Wife already suspects.
How long until son does, too?
Go fuck yourself, Darkblood.
This'll do.
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah... ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah... ♪
♪ Don't-don't-don't-
don't get captured... ♪
♪ Ca-ca-ca-captured ♪
♪ Don't-don't-don't
don't-don't-don't ♪
♪ Don't get-get-get ♪
♪ Get-get-get-get-get ♪
♪ Good day from the house
of the haunted ♪
♪ Get a job, get a house
get a coffin ♪
♪ Don't stray from the path
Remain where you at ♪
♪ That maximizes our profit ♪
♪ Is that blunt?
Oh well, hell, so's this boot ♪
♪ We live to hear you say
Please don't shoot ♪
♪ A pure delight
c'mon, make my night... ♪
♪...till your last sane thought
take flight ♪
♪ What a great sight
what a job, what a good life ♪
♪ The more we act wrong
the more we are right... ♪
There you are.
♪...Some call it work
but it's more like an art ♪
♪ We just paint the walls
with your heart ♪
♪ And we better not catch you ♪
♪ He in here, me in here
we in here ♪
♪ Don't get captured ♪
♪ No cryin' here ♪
♪ Just do your dirt
and disappear ♪
♪ Don't get captured ♪
♪ Then lay it low
take it slow, and reappear ♪
♪ Don't get captured... ♪
Hello, brother.
You must be hungry.
♪ Don't get captured ♪
♪ Don't get captured... ♪
See you soon.
Hey, Tin-man!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
were you napping?
I was defragmenting, Rex.
Okay, well, quit it.
You don't want to miss this.
Welcome to our new digs, baby.
I can't believe
I'm actually here.
Huh.
Whoa.
Good to be home again.
If I have to hear one more time
about how
you're an original member
of the Guardians
of the Globe...
You'll do what, exactly?
I dunno,
probably explode something.
Ooh!
Maybe your nuts?
Is it weird
that I'm nervous?
No.
I am, too.
Pick up your jaws.
You're not tourists.
This isn't a holy site.
This is your job.
The sooner you get up to speed,
the sooner people stop dying.
Hey, Cecil.
Uh...
you missed a spot?
Left that one there
as a reminder.
When you
prove yourselves worthy
of the heroes
who came before you,
it'll get cleaned off.
Until then, stare at it
whenever you think
you're hot shit.
Sir, Omni-Man is here.
He's asking to see you.
Settle in.
We'll talk later.
We're cool, right?
What?
Oh, you mean
after you knocked out
three of my teeth
and gave me a concussion
in front of the entire
superhero community?
Mm, you did kinda ask for it.
Yeah...
I guess I did,
but you know what,
all those other heroes,
total assholes anyway.
Huge assholes, right?
Oh, yeah, gaping, dirty,
filthy assholes...
Okay, that's fine.
Rex, please do not allow
your personal
and professional lives
to intersect.
Alienating Atom Eve
was the direct result
of your lapse in judgment.
Do not repeat it
with Monster Girl.
Tell you what,
when you grow a pair, Robot,
you can tell me
how to swing mine.
This isn't relationship
advice, Rex.
This is an order.
What, are you crazy, man?
She looks like she's 14!
Besides,
now that I'm a Guardian,
I can bang anyone I want.
Good.
I'm glad we have
an understanding.
Ow!
What the hell?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I must have pinched a nerve.
I forget how soft humans are.
Hey, you've been
working all night.
You're one to talk.
Where were you?
Eh, the usual.
Teaching someone a lesson.
How about we go to bed?
Nolan...
Okay, what's going on?
Nothing.
Just... work stuff.
Come on,
you're the wife
of the most powerful man
on Earth.
You shouldn't have
to deal with work stuff.
Did you seriously say that?
What?
I'm not just your wife, Nolan.
That's why
I deal with work stuff.
I like dealing with work stuff.
Yeah, and I love that
about you...
Oh, please,
don't give me that shit.
Shh...
Don't you dare shush me...
Nolan!
No... Nolan.
Hey.
Sorry.
I meant to teleport
to your front door,
but this thing isn't exactly
Swiss in its precision.
I almost killed you.
Yeah, I noticed.
Didn't expect you
on me so fast.
Yeah, I'm a little jumpy.
Maybe you can understand that.
Why are you here, Cecil?
That was the best night
of my life.
I mean, no one's done
a study yet,
but I feel safe going out
on a limb here and...
Too much?
Yeah...
but I like it.
I expect to feel
the same way next time.
When you plan the date.
That...
sounds like a commitment
to a second date?
♪ Let's do this right
let's do this right ♪
♪ Let's go to paradise ♪
♪ This shit feel like
Friday nights... ♪
Goodnight, Mark Grayson.
♪ Feel like we in paradise ♪
♪ Paradise... ♪
Yes!
Whoo-hoo!
♪ But I swear I've never
loved you more... ♪
Hey...
Uh, what's going on?
NASA's about to launch
the first manned mission
to Mars.
Yeah, I saw that.
It's cool.
I need your father
to shadow the mission
and make sure
nothing goes wrong.
Only, he won't do it.
I'm busy training
my son, Cecil,
and with the Guardians gone,
I'm needed here on Earth.
If I didn't know better,
I'd say you were
trying to get rid of me.
It's because of
the Guardians' massacre
that I want you
on this mission.
The planet needs
a win right now,
and this is it.
You think people
are gonna care about Mars
if there's an attack
on Earth,
and I'm not here
to save them?
I think they're gonna care
if the first four people
to walk on another world
end up dying there.
My priority is to my family
and this planet.
End of story.
I guess this is the part
where I volunteer?
I mean, that's what happened
last time you came here
asking Dad to go to space.
Yeah, that was the moon, Mark.
That hardly counts as space...
You were just teaching me
I've got responsibilities.
Isn't this one of them?
Your responsibilities
are bigger
than four astronauts,
and Cecil
didn't ask you to go.
He asked me.
If the kid wants to go,
he'd be doing humanity a favor.
Debbie, help me out here.
I don't like
Mark missing school,
but I can't think
of a better reason
than keeping people safe.
How much school
am I really gonna miss?
I can zip up to Mars
and be back tomorrow.
The fact that you don't know
how far away Mars is,
is exactly why
you shouldn't be missing school.
It's a two-week mission.
Two weeks?
Dad's right, I'm not ready.
Things with Amber
are going really well.
Sweetheart...
Lots of people
are going to tell you
how to use your powers,
but it's up to you
to make these decisions.
You need to decide
what kind of hero
you want to be.
I'll do it.
Well, pack a lunch, kid.
You leave tomorrow.
Sir, we wanted
Nolan off-planet
so we could investigate him
for the murders
without arousing his suspicion.
What does sending Mark away
get us?
A chance to see
what this kid can do,
and more importantly,
if his heart's
in the right place.
And if it isn't?
One nightmare scenario
is enough to worry about
right now, Donald.
I don't want to lie
to Amber,
but I can't tell her
the truth either.
This is why dating
regular people
is a pain in the ass.
Sure, but it's not like
dating Rex worked out...
Changing the subject now.
As much as I'd love to help
with your very special crisis,
I've got my own crap
to deal with now.
I'll make you a deal.
You help me
with my Amber stuff,
I'll help you
with your Rex stuff...
It's not just Rex, Mark.
It's everything.
It's my parents,
and school, and college,
and I don't know
if being a superhero
is what I want to do
right now.
But what else would you do?
I don't know.
That's the problem.
I guess...
If you need anything
or want to talk about it,
I'm here.
After I get back from Mars,
I mean.
Thanks.
Look, once you tell someone
your secret identity,
that's it.
So if you're going
to tell Amber the truth,
you'd better be serious
about her.
Are you serious
about her, Mark?
...the weather
continues to hold
and we've been told
everything's looking good
as we enter
the last few minutes
before the launch...
...of the Mars mission shuttle.
Mark?
I figured
you'd need something
to store
your rice separator in,
and I found some extra change
in the couch, so...
That's very thoughtful.
Thank you.
Come on in.
Listen, um, Amber.
I'm, uh...
I'm...
You're what?
Volunteering,
just like you.
I'm-I'm going away
and helping people
for two weeks.
What?
Like far away.
Well, that's great.
When?
...just under
60 seconds to launch...
Um...
Any minute now.
- For real?
- More or less.
Where are you going?
You know, it's desert-y.
Hardly anyone goes there, um...
There's almost no buildings
or anything.
You don't know
where you're going?
I signed up last minute.
...the firing sequence
is armed and ready...
Amber, you're incredible,
and you make me want to be
a better person,
so at the risk of sounding
totally desperate,
please don't lose interest in me
while I'm gone.
I figure you've banked
about two weeks
of interest...
Ten, nine, eight, seven...
Maybe three.
...six, five, four, three...
I'll bring you back
a souvenir!
...two, one...
And we have lift-off
of the Mars mission.
an international exploration
of the red planet
that will broaden
humanity's knowledge
in ways we can only imagine.
Whoa.
Cool.
Cutting it close, kid.
I'm here, aren't I?
Yeah, you are.
Okay, first thing,
stay out of sight
unless something goes wrong.
This is supposed to be a win
for human spaceflight.
I'm a ghost.
Second,
the main reason
you're on this mission
is the Martians...
What, there are Martians?
Where'd you think
Martian Man came from, Jupiter?
Uh, I...
never thought about it.
We don't know
much about 'em,
but we know
they live underground
and keep to themselves.
You shouldn't have any trouble.
Just keep an eye out.
Martians.
Way to bury the lede, Cecil.
Actually the lede
is "Make sure our astronauts
get home safe.
Humanity's counting on you."
Ugh.
It's a waste of Mark's time.
It was his decision,
and I'm proud of him.
Isn't this
what superpowers are for?
He doesn't understand
his responsibilities.
He's 17, Nolan.
He hasn't had responsibilities
before now.
You know, ever since
Mark got his powers,
you've been different.
I'm trying to teach him.
You've been distant,
annoyed at everything,
and you've been mean.
I've been under
a lot of stress!
You've been talking about home.
You never talk about home.
I want Mark to know his people.
I don't even know your people.
I've never even met
another Viltrumite.
I've told you...
You-you've told me stories, yes,
but that's not the same.
You're hiding something from me,
and it hurts.
Okay, I'm-I'm sorry.
I didn't... I'm not...
You're not what?
I never thought
I would have a family,
and then you came along,
and I love you
and Mark
so much,
but when I see Mark
with his powers,
and after what happened
to the Guardians,
I'm terrified
I could lose everything.
Me too.
So what do we do?
Well, Mark's gone
for two weeks.
And?
Remember our first trip
together?
Nolan, I...
I told Olga
I'd sell her house.
Her house will still be here
when we get back.
Hey, you asked me
what we do.
We do this.
Pack a lunch, my ass.
Sweetie...
L'Osteria Donato!
I can't believe
it's still here!
Oh, we'll never get in.
I made reservations.
You never make reservations.
Whoa...
We are down, Houston.
It's a beautiful day on Mars,
and a beautiful accomplishment
for all humankind.
Nice job, Hank.
Did you guys see that?
See what?
Eh, never mind.
Ah, maybe not the best
color scheme for this mission.
Gah... this sucks.
Maybe they have a charger
in the shuttle?
What?
Shit...
Julius Caesar,
one of Earth's
greatest conquerors,
reduced to that.
I think Caesar's doing
just fine history-wise.
Yeah, I suppose.
God, this takes me back...
It was only a few years ago.
Our first date
was 20 years ago, Nolan.
Huh.
Mostly, I remember you
dumping me right after.
Well, yeah, because
you were a dick.
Come on,
I flew you to Rome.
Yeah, and you
expected me to worship you
because of it.
I was new here.
I got better.
You know what,
you only got a second date
because I saw you
save those kids on the news.
I'm glad we came.
But you still feel
something's wrong.
Don't you?
I don't know if it's
what happened to the Guardians,
or Mark,
or if it's just us,
but I feel like I'm standing
on the edge of a cliff,
and I'm the only one of us
who can't fly.
I haven't been honest
with you, Debbie.
About what?
About the murders.
Nolan?
Cecil thinks
I had something to do with...
what happened to the Guardians.
But you didn't.
I'm the only survivor,
and I'm not human,
and Cecil's never liked me.
You have to talk to him.
I've tried.
This could get bad.
Oh, god...
What do we do?
We stay together as a family.
You, me, and Mark.
All you have to do is trust me.
Nolan!
Do you trust me, Debbie?
There's-there's a dragon
behind you!
Please.
Do you trust me?
I trust you.
You have no idea
how much I needed
to hear you say that.
Okay, now do something!
I'm on vacation
with my beautiful wife.
Let Cecil earn his paycheck.
Hmm...
You can come out.
I'm not hiding.
Cecil.
Nolan warned us about you.
Shouldn't have any trouble.
Martians live underground.
Hmm...
No, no, no, no!
Ah, Jesus...
The hell...?
Huh?
Do not move, human.
Whoa!
Hold on!
I'm-I'm not here
to hurt anyone, okay?
I'm just here
looking for, uh...
You guys need to keep
your dogs on a leash!
I assume those are, like,
Martian dogs, or something?
You are unaffected
by the sequids?
No, I am very affected by them.
I can still taste them.
The other humans,
in white,
are they like you?
The astronauts?
I mean, kinda,
but not exactly.
Wait, you know where they are?
And you speak English?
We speak Martian.
Welcome to Mars, Earth-man.
Thanks for having me...
Mars-man.
Mr. Mars-Man.
Sir.
Your Highness?
What is your purpose here?
It's funny, uh,
I was sent to protect
some of my fellow Earth-men
on a mission
to your lovely planet,
and if they don't get back
in one piece,
I'm really gonna
look like a dick.
Oh, hey, guys.
Uh, yeah, we don't know
who that is.
It was a secret mission.
Well, you suck at it then.
Mistakes were made,
but everything's
back on track,
so if you don't mind,
we'll get out
of your, um, hair,
and maybe keep
your little squid-dogs
under control this time?
The sequids
are the very reason
I captured your people.
They are
a world-destroying race
who left a trail of destruction
across the universe,
before crashing onto our planet.
Alone, their group mind
is scattered and weak,
but with an appropriate host,
they become unified
and unstoppable.
Our shape-changing abilities
let us resist them,
but if a single sequid
fuses with one of your people,
they would rise up as one
and savage Mars,
and soon after,
Earth.
Oh.
Tell me, Earth-man,
how are you able
to resist them?
I'm part Viltrumite.
Ever heard of us?
I am the Emperor of Mars!
Of course, I've heard of you!
Okay, well then,
you know we like to help out
wherever we can,
which is why I was sent
to protect these astronauts,
so if you're all good,
we'll finish our science
and head home...
Impossible!
The humans are scheduled
for immediate execution.
We cannot risk them
coming in contact with a sequid.
I understand.
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Grab hands!
Move, move, move!
- Coolant levels.
- Check!
- Oxygen levels.
- Check.
Fuck it!
Let's do this.
Ha, ha, ha!
Huh?
Um, okay.
Can I lift that?
I think I can lift that.
Ow! Shit!
Ow! Ow!
Come on, guys!
No hard feelings, right?
I'm gonna take a rock
if that's okay.
Yeah?
I've been
wanting to go to Mars
since I was a kid.
Now I never want
to go back.
Never
would be too soon.
...the world's
spirits were raised
as the first men and women
to walk on another planet
returned home
after a by-the-book mission...
Oh, hey, you're...
back early.
Wow.
Uh... how was Mars?
By the looks of it,
less eventful than
whatever was happening here.
We'd love to hear more
over dinner.
Sweetie?
We're having chicken.
Mark!
That's the response
I was hoping for.
Wait, you were gone?
So, how was it?
Well, mostly boring.
Encountered
some local wildlife.
Met the king,
kind of a jerk.
Oh, but I did
actually help people.
Not sure how grateful they were,
but whatever.
Huh.
That is a strangely
non-specific story.
Check it out,
I got you something.
Ooh, I've always wanted
one of these.
It's, um...
Ugh!
What do they call them?
A...
Rock.
...rock?
And not just any rock.
A M-earth rock.
It's an Earth rock.
Whoa... even more impressive.
Yeah, just make sure
you never show it
to any geologists,
or anyone who knows
anything about rocks.
They might tell you
something crazy.
Well, thank you.
For the beautiful,
regular Earth rock.
Guess what Donald found
when we searched your office?
Hmm...
Disappointment?
Dried blood.
Not much,
but enough to run for DNA.
Hmm.
The Guardians.
Yup.
Planted.
Didn't kill Guardians.
Didn't try to kill Nolan.
I know.
But I have to do this anyway.
Why?
Because you didn't listen to me
when I told you
to drop the goddamn case.
Can't excise me.
Destroyed the book
you need for ritual
centuries ago.
The Demonius Ex Mortum?
I had a few of my guys
reconstruct it.
They used artificial
intelligence
to figure out
the missing words.
Technology, am I right?
"Dominari daemonium meam.
Mitte ad inferos..."
Never thought you'd be the one
to protect him.
See, that's the problem
with demons,
you only see good and evil.
Black and white.
Well, I need to keep things gray
until I can figure out
why Nolan killed the Guardians
and how to stop him.
Say I'd see you in Hell,
but there's a worse place
waiting for you.
...daemonium meam...
...ad inferos...
Um...
Oh, now you care
about the demon?
He's not dead,
he's just back in hell.
Isn't...
Isn't that worse?
This place is amazing.
Why did they decide to sell?
The wife had
an opportunity abroad.
Oh, that's nice.
I think we want it.
I'll start the paperwork.
Finally, phase one begins.
I know.
Two more sales
and I'll break
the monthly record.
If anyone can do it,
it's you.
Oh, did you talk to Cecil?
Yeah, get this,
some new evidence came up,
and apparently,
I'm in the clear.
He even apologized.
Cecil never apologizes.
I know.
So nothing to worry about.
Everything's fine.