[explosion]
Guys! Help me!
Mark?
[Mark] You can't tell anyone?
Where the hell did you go?
This isn't what it looks like.
Wait! Amber!
[roars]
[Robot] Your recovery
was tenuous at times.
You stayed with me?
I never left.
You know how hard it is
to grow cells this quickly?
You will receive the schematics
when you finish your work.
[Mauler] We need some insurance.
This is the oldest blood
on the suit.
Nolan struck first.
[Debbie] Why did you do it?
[Nolan] I didn't do anything.
[Debbie roars]
Fuck you, Nolan.
[birds chirping]
[sighs]
[♪♪♪]
["I Like Myself (Most Of
The Time)" by K.Flay plays]
♪ I like myself
most of the time... ♪
Amber, listen,
I can explain
everything, just--
[turns up car radio volume]
♪ ...Most of the time... ♪
[♪♪♪]
♪ I like myself
most of the time ♪
♪ Is that a crime? ♪
[beans grinding]
♪ Even planet Earth
took seven days... ♪
[water boiling]
♪ Even if it looks real ♪
♪ You can fake it
in a million different ways ♪
♪ Nobody chose
to have their face ♪
♪ But you're stuck with it... ♪
[yawns]
Ow, ow, ow!
♪ So rather than counting
my curses ♪
♪ I try to stay positive ♪
[♪♪♪]
♪ I don't think I'm perfect ♪
♪ But I've got
some things together ♪
♪ I see photos of proposals ♪
♪ That I know
are empty gestures ♪
♪ Get a grip... ♪
♪ You only got one shot
let 'er rip ♪
♪ Take a dip, have a smoke ♪
♪ Try to laugh at the jokes ♪
♪ Ha! ♪
♪ I like myself
most of the time ♪
♪ Is that a crime? ♪
[♪♪♪]
♪ I like myself
most of the time... ♪
Why did you keep it?
I used it to take care
of Damien Darkblood,
but maybe part of me
wanted you to find it, too.
After 20 years together,
I deserve to know the truth.
[sighs]
I wanted to tell you
months ago.
But you didn't.
Was someone controlling you?
Were you--
were you blackmailed?
Did they threaten me
or Mark?
No.
Then why?
You need to trust me.
If you can do that,
we'll be okay.
Mark too.
Everything will be fine.
Trust you?
How could I possibly
trust you now?
Because you know me.
There's a lot of things
I thought I knew about you.
The Guardians
were our friends.
They were good people.
They saved lives.
They had families.
You killed them.
I had no choice.
I don't believe that.
You said you wanted
to tell me months ago,
but you're still
not telling me now.
No, I don't trust you.
Not anymore.
You broke that.
If you don't have
anything else to say,
you need to leave.
Debbie--
Get out of my house.
You don't mean that.
[grunts angrily]
Get out of my house!
We'll talk later.
[smashing]
[crows cawing]
[line ringing]
[Mark's voice] Hey...
Mark? It's Mom.
Listen to me--
[Mark's voicemail continues]
--I'm not around.
You could leave a message,
but wouldn't you rather
text me instead?
[beep]
Mark, it's Mom.
Come home. Please--
[Debbie gasps]
Debbie, I'm sorry,
but you have to come with us.
There's no time.
Thanks, William.
See you later.
Bye, Amber.
Amber!
Uh...
Come on, this is dumb.
No, what's dumb
is how long I've been putting up
with your bullshit.
[groans]
You're right.
I've been an asshole,
and I'm sorry
I didn't realize that sooner,
but that all stops today.
[key turns in lock]
Amber...
Uh...
Oh, here we go...
Amber, I'm in--
[slam]
[gasps] Oh, my god!
It's okay.
This is why I'm always late,
or why I don't show,
because I'm off saving lives,
or stopping some bad guys, or...
going to Mars.
[chuckles]
I wanted to tell you
so many times.
Uh...
did you hear what I just said?
[groans]
I know you're a superhero.
You know...
Y-you know?
I'm not an idiot.
I figured it out weeks ago.
Then why are we fighting?
We're fighting
because you lied to me.
You made me feel stupid
and unimportant--
It's a secret identity!
--and because
you don't trust me.
I'm trusting you now!
Oh, my god.
I mean, it's cute
you think that's enough.
But Amber...
Fly away, flyboy,
or take the stairs.
I really don't give a shit.
I'd like to be alone.
[sighs]
[whooshes away]
[Monster Girl calls] Hello?
Hmm, so much for "welcome back."
Congrats for not dying
when a giant space cat
gave you brain surgery.
[rocket fires]
[lights snap]
-There she is!
-It's so good to see you!
[laughing]
Haha, there's our girl!
-Hey, hey!
-Hey, Monster Girl!
Welcome back!
[party music plays]
She returns victorious!
Well, well, well,
it's about time
you dragged
your lazy ass back here.
I was getting pretty tired
of hanging out with these dorks
all by myself.
We start partying now.
It's 10:00 a.m.
We're the Guardians
of the Globe, baby.
If we can die at any time,
uh, we can drink
at any time.
I put your picture on the side!
Ha. Ha.
Cute.
But I'm lactose intolerant.
Whoa, hold on.
Do you know me at all?
I filled them with beer.
You're welcome.
Guess how long
it took him to do that?
And how much milk
he wasted.
I poured it all down the drain.
Why are you never
this industrious
when it involves training?
[chuckles]
How come I get
my head beat in,
and it's a week
in the hospital.
You get your head beat in,
and your powers come back?
I figure it's karma
for putting up with this guy.
You're welcome.
[laughs]
I am delighted at
your recovery, Monster Girl.
Very much.
I wouldn't be recovered
if it wasn't for you.
You saved my life.
Of course.
I would never let you die.
Die. Die. Die.
[voice speeds up, glitching]
Die. Die. Die. Die. Die.
[rapid, robotic]
Die. Die. Die. Die--
[voice speeding
into percussive buzz]
[footsteps retreating]
My apologies.
A small programming error.
Soon to be fixed permanently.
[laughing]
Holy shit!
Well, that was creepy.
That was like
the creepiest thing
I've seen you do since--
[gasps] Do you remember
that time
I caught you operating
on your own head?
I swear to god,
he had his head
on the bench,
and he was just
standing over it,
prying it open with
a Phillips head screwdriver.
Oh, my god.
Can I get another...
[radio interference
squeals and crackles]
You!
Get out of the truck.
[fires, glass cracks]
[grunts]
I said, get out of the--
Huh?
[hydraulics whirring]
Step back,
please.
[hydraulics whirr, metal clanks]
[pipes detach, hissing]
[Robot] Gentlemen.
[groans in disgust]
-What is that?
-[gags] Ugh.
[Robot] Come, now,
I believe you can answer
that question on your own.
It's the real Robot.
[metal pincers clap]
Well done.
Perhaps
you're the original, then?
We've been growing you
a new body.
And now introductions
are complete,
show me your work.
[metal legs clank and whirr]
[Robot] It's perfect.
We are professionals.
[Robot] Except for
the timed-release
mycotoxin sacs,
the embedded cortical override,
and the seven--
oh, sorry, eight,
synaptic transceivers.
Maybe I'm old-fashioned,
but I prefer to be
the only person
in control of my body.
Please.
I would have been disappointed
if you hadn't tried.
Remove all of that,
add in this small upgrade
of my own design,
and we can discuss your payment.
Let's discuss our payment
and we'll do all of that.
A Global Defense Agency
control collar
placates
the strongest of wills.
A highly-restricted technology.
It's encrypted.
Besides, a little trust
goes a long way.
Actions go further.
[cutters whine, circuits snap]
[crumbling]
[Robot] There.
I am alone and helpless.
Sheesh.
Alone, yes.
Helpless, I doubt it.
Do what he wants.
[Robot]
It needs to be placed on the--
Upper brainstem.
I recognize a neural-link
when I see one.
[William]
Yesterday was messed up.
I mean, is Rick
ever gonna be okay?
God...
What that Sinclair guy
was doing to people...
Cecil's team
knows what they're doing.
They'll help Rick.
I gotta say it--
If you had helped me find him
right away,
none of this
would have ever happened.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I suck.
It figures,
I finally fall for someone,
and then... boom.
Cyborg.
So this is why
I've hardly seen you
the last six months.
Because you're a superhero.
Not anymore.
What? Why?
Because I'm a terrible friend
and a worse boyfriend.
Because I'm gonna fail
my last year of high school.
Because I got everything
I ever wanted,
and I messed it all up.
I should've listened to my dad.
Your dad?
Omni-Man.
Oh.
Of course.
Your dad's Omni-Man.
How did I never see that?
I am such a screw-up.
[William] Okay, stop.
Enough with the sulking,
you big baby.
What?
You can fly.
You're invulnerable.
Your dad's the greatest
superhero on Earth,
and your mom loves
and cares about you.
You just need to study,
and you can pull up your grades.
But you were
a terrible boyfriend to Amber,
and you got what you deserved.
Sorry, not sorry.
If I can deal with almost losing
the hottest guy I've ever had,
you can deal with this.
What?
Friends tell friends the truth.
Not like that, they don't!
I just got dumped, dude!
You got dumped weeks ago,
you just didn't realize it.
You're like a bad guy
in a samurai movie
who gets cut in half,
but thinks they're fine
until they're like, "Oh, my god,
my top half's sliding away
from my bottom half."
[mock groaning]
I love you, man,
but I need someone else
to talk to.
[indistinct chatter]
Debbie?
Good.
We need to talk about--
Nolan killed
the Guardians of the Globe.
I know.
[slap]
How could you know
and not tell me?
I couldn't risk Nolan
finding out we knew.
Not until we figured out
what he was doing
and how to stop him.
We failed on both those counts,
by the way.
What do you mean, stop him?
Do you mean kill him?
Cecil--
[Cecil] I'm not sure
we could kill him.
Not us, anyway.
[sighs heavily]
There's only one person I know
who might be able to go
toe-to-toe with Omni-Man
and come out on top, Debbie.
No.
No. Never.
You can't.
Where's Mark, Debbie?
Where's--
[exhales sadly]
Mark...
I killed
the Guardians of the Globe.
Wait, before you say anything,
just listen.
Please.
I'm not a monster.
I didn't want to do it...
but it had to be done.
It was my responsibility.
Other people
won't understand that,
but I know you can.
What I'm about to tell you
will change everything.
Just remember, you're my son,
and I love you and your mother
more than...
[sighs]
What am I doing?
[drill whirring]
Ugh. Disgusting.
I didn't design it
to be drained,
or ever opened.
What changed?
I met someone.
Make room, please.
[hatch blows]
[mechanisms whirr]
[retracts wetly]
[gasps, wincing]
[voice weakened]
Hurry, please.
Air is toxic to me.
It burns my-- my lungs.
[breath wheezing]
[gags] Yuck...
Don't make a face.
You lost the coin toss.
[wheezing]
This will be painful.
[Robot chuckles ruefully]
My entire life
has been painful.
[device whirring]
You realize
this procedure doesn't
transfer you to the new body.
It creates a copy of your mind.
For you, nothing will change.
For him, everything will.
I... understand.
Three, two...
[power surging]
[coughing and choking]
[circuits crackle]
Of course, his brain's abnormal.
You didn't think of that?
Look at him!
Shut up, will you?
His motor cortex
is the size of a pea.
Same for his occipital
and parietal lobes.
They've all been eaten alive
by his oversized cerebrum.
[gasping weakly]
The system wasn't designed
for neurons this dense.
Are you calling us stupid?
Yes.
I'm calling us stupid.
Compensating now,
but it's gonna be close.
[gasping]
[groaning]
[both groaning]
[power surging and crackling]
Idiot!
You just lost us
our control collars.
Just get the fire extinguisher
before we lose everything else.
[screaming in agony]
[groans]
[grunts]
Which...
Which am I?
See?
It's not just us.
You won the coin toss, champ.
You're the new one.
I...
wasn't expecting this.
This feeling of continuance.
I closed my eyes...
and opened new ones.
I didn't know which one I'd be.
That's how it works.
We had to make it seamless,
otherwise one of us knows
he's the clone,
and that never ends well.
In your case,
it's a little more obvious,
but it looks like that problem
took care of itself.
[coughing]
Oh, shit, here we go.
I'm sorry it wasn't you.
D-Don't be.
Be... happy.
Change the... [wheezing]
...world.
Experience everything...
we never could.
[wheezing]
What are you...
w-waiting for?
This was always the plan.
[gasping]
I can put you back in the pod.
We can both survive.
Change the world together.
[wheezing]
This is...
what I want.
Please.
[gasps a ragged final breath]
It was an act of mercy.
We know.
We do it all the time.
Now... [clears throat]
our schematics.
The cryptographic key
is the entire text
of Frankenstein.
Look who has
a sense of humor after all.
And now that our deal
is complete,
it's time you both
returned to prison.
[laughing]
He's serious.
Yeah, he's also a teenage boy.
No, I'm a 30-year old genius
in a teenage boy's body,
with a neural-link chip
you just installed for me.
[chuckles]
That was your plan?
My plan was not to hurt you,
but here we are.
[slam]
[hydraulics whirr]
[footsteps rumbling]
Mark?
Debbie?
[sighs]
What did you do?
[floorboard creaks]
[gasps, struggling]
Cecil...
[struggling]
[splashing]
[gunfire rattling]
[soldiers groan]
[weapons cocking]
[gunfire rattling]
[grunts]
[limbs splashing]
[gasps,
weapon falls, clattering]
[explosion]
[screams]
[♪♪♪]
[groaning]
Oh, shit.
[yelps]
Nolan, wait.
Just wait--
You've been spying on me?
On my family?
It-it was
for your family's protection.
You were always
so pathetic, Donald.
Cecil's little lapdog.
-[grunts]
-Run now!
[grunting]
[firing]
Oh, shit.
[metal crumpling]
[groans]
[crunching]
[gasps]
It's been an honor, sir.
Huh.
Who are you talking to--
The honor was all mine.
Oh, no...
Oh, god.
Nolan?
You monster.
He's not dead.
Even after evacuating
the neighborhood,
we had to keep
the yield down.
Best it'll do
is knock him on his ass
for an hour or two--
or maybe not even
hurt him at all.
He's going to find Mark.
I don't know
who Nolan is anymore.
what he's going to do.
Me neither.
So we'd better
find Mark first.
Huh?
Hey, Eve.
[Eve] Oh...
So I'm helping you today.
[♪♪♪]
♪ The God killer
This Tokyo and I'm Godzilla ♪
♪ Playing blackjack
versus death... ♪
All of this conflict
and destruction
is pure theater.
You will come with me
back to prison.
♪ ...but I'm a god figure... ♪
You double-crossed us,
you vat-grown piece of shit!
♪ ...Murdered and robbed ♪
♪ This is Bonaparte
and he paying with Toussaint ♪
♪ And they went on
a world conquest... ♪
Is that kind of language
really necessary?
And you're both clones as well.
Exactly,
and one advantage
to being a clone-- [grunts]
--we always know
what the other one is thinking.
♪ You say that
you'll love me, ay ♪
♪ I'm guessing I'ma be okay... ♪
[gasps]
♪ You say that you don't
feel me now ♪
♪ I feel like
I'ma live somehow ♪
♪ Your love never meant much
to me, ay... ♪
[grunts]
[gasps]
[cackling]
[trigger clicks]
Huh?
Very clever,
but you don't have
nearly enough equipment
to do that again.
[Robot's weapon surging]
[grunts]
[Cecil]
All Guardians to HQ.
Apocalypse level priority.
He's right.
What do you want to do?
I want to break his stupid face,
even though we just
finished making it.
I'll keep his machine busy.
On three.
One, two, three!
[exploding crash]
Huh?
[yelps]
[brakes screech]
What the hell was that?
[William stammering] O-Omni--
Uh, Mr. Grayson...
Are you okay?
You look kinda, uh...
recently on fire.
[pats car roof]
Where's Mark, William?
You were supposed
to drop him off an hour ago.
Uh, Amber dumped him,
and he didn't like my advice,
so he went to go find Eve.
Call him.
His phone's broken.
There was this attack
at the college, and--
and all of a sudden, we were--
[metal crunches above]
Where's Eve?
Uh...
Mark said she got a place
out in the woods,
a couple hundred miles
west of here.
That's not...
blood on you, is it?
Bye?
Look, be quiet!
Just sit tight
until I call on you,
and hope to hell
I don't have to.
Sit tight?
Hey, we're not your kids
in the back seat
while you run in
to buy cigarettes, Cecil.
What the hell's going on?
I said, sit tight.
Oh, come on.
I mean, come on!
For once, you're right.
We need to know
what's happening.
Robot, can't you do
a little hacking
and find out
what's going down?
Oh great.
The hits just keep on comin'.
Look who crashed again.
[chuckles] Okay.
You know, we'll all be lucky
if murderbot here
doesn't strangle us all
in our sleep.
Hello! Robot!
Hello, anybody home?
You know what he needs?
He needs one of those
spinning ball things
so we know he's still alive.
I'm very much alive,
more so now than ever.
What the fuck?
Who the hell are you?
You all know me as Robot,
but my real name
is Rudolph Connors,
though I'd prefer
if you called me Rudy.
The Robot you knew before
was simply a drone
I controlled remotely.
What?
How do we know
you're telling the truth?
Ask me something
only Robot would know.
Why the fuck
do you look like me?
How the fuck
That is a much longer story.
One that can wait
until whatever crisis this is
has been resolved--
No, no, no,
forget the crisis.
You can explain now.
[GDA Agent] I've got 'em!
Invincible and Atom Eve.
Approximately 300 miles away,
traveling north-west
over Rideout National Forest.
Sir,
Omni-Man's closing in
on their location.
Estimated time to intercept--
six minutes.
Shit.
Can't you use your teleporter?
To bring Mark and Eve
back here?
You need to be wearing
one of these,
and it can't do us
all at once.
We need to buy some time first.
Let's bring the hammer down.
[Eve groans]
That sucks.
I'm sorry you got dumped.
I thought
once I told her the truth,
we'd be good.
[sighs]
Stupid.
A little naive, maybe.
Hey, you're the one
who told me
not to tell Amber
I was Invincible.
Yeah, but I didn't tell you
to string her along
for five months
while being an asshole about it.
I thought you'd figure
that part out yourself.
Oh, my god.
I haven't figured out anything.
I don't know who I am,
who I'm supposed to be...
Yeah, took me a while, too.
I was with Teen Team
for three years,
and with Rex
for much longer than that.
And now you're... this.
Uh, I'm still Atom Eve,
and I've saved more lives
in the last three days
than I did
in the last three years.
[groans] Sorry.
I didn't mean it like that.
Um, and trust me,
being out here is an upgrade
to living with my parents.
I should call my mom, though.
You wouldn't dare.
[thundering explosion]
[man] Okay, we've got him.
He's down.
[distant cawing]
[thudding of bodies]
Hit him again.
[energy charging]
[roars]
400 billion dollars
for the world's
most expensive nosebleed.
Omni-Man is back on course
to intercept Invincible
and Atom Eve.
[sighs heavily]
Power up the teleporter.
You said we couldn't
teleport them yet.
It's not for them.
Then I received Cecil's alert,
and left for here
as quickly as I could.
Any questions?
Uh, yeah, a few!
First, why me?
I mean, sure,
I get that anyone
would want to be me,
but why specifically me?
And second,
why a kid version of me?
That's just weird.
Exactly.
It's messed up.
You didn't even ask first.
[Rex] That's what you think
is wrong with this?
There is so much
wrong with this.
He did it for me.
What?
What are you even
talking about?
We were both prisoners
in our own bodies.
Monster Girl slowly
getting younger,
and me trapped
in a mechanical tomb
of my own creation.
I escaped my prison.
Now I'll help you
escape yours.
No!
Don't give him any sympathy!
He still hasn't told me
why he stole my kid face!
You're ruining my childhood,
and that's hard
because it already sucked.
I adapted your DNA
because I noticed
Monster Girl found you...
interesting.
What?
Wait, what?
Oh, my God--
I don't even know
how to feel about that!
Goddamit, Robot!
Will you please
stop fucking me up?
[Monster Girl]
So, you lied to us
about who you really were,
freed the Maulers from prison,
stole Rex's DNA,
conspired with criminals
to grow yourself a new body,
and you expect us all to be
like, "Oh sure, who wouldn't?"
I-- Yes.
I mean, I... did.
[sighs]
I need time to process this.
I bet everyone else does, too.
Ya think?
Hey!
I know why Cecil's
holding us at high alert.
What the fuck is going on today?
[explosions booming]
[gasps]
What is that?
Huh, I'll tell you
what that is,
not our problem anymore.
We should check in with Cecil.
Forget it.
I'm done with all that.
So are you.
That's not why I came out here.
You came out here
to get away from Rex
and all that superhero bullshit.
Rex had nothing
to do with this.
I came out here because
I needed to start over,
but that doesn't mean
ignoring the world
when it needs me.
The world was fine
before I came along.
It'll be fine
without my help.
Better, probably.
I get that
you're feeling shitty
because Amber dumped you,
but trust me,
you'll feel worse
if you sit here and do nothing
when you could save lives.
I doubt it.
Fine,
but I'm going.
[sonic boom rumbles]
[grunts]
You thought that could hurt me?
No.
That was just
to get your attention.
[growls]
[teleporter whoosh]
[panting]
[chuckles]
Jesus, Nolan,
right for the throat?
After everything
that we've been through?
Keep out of this, Cecil.
[rocks crumbling]
[teleporter whoosh]
You know I can't do that, Nolan.
[grunts]
[teleporter whoosh]
[pants, chuckling]
I've faced death more times
than I can count,
but I'll be damned
if that didn't put my balls
in my throat.
[teleporter whoosh]
I just wanna know why.
Every one of the Guardians
risked their necks for you,
over and over again.
I never needed their help.
They were weak.
They were your friends,
and so was I...
which is why I know
you didn't kill them
for the fun of it.
You had a reason.
You wanna get it off your chest?
[claps, shockwave rumbling]
[teleporter whooshes]
Fine, don't tell me,
but what about Debbie, huh?
Doesn't she deserve an answer?
Don't say her name.
Why not?
You hurt her, not me.
She and I have that
in common now.
I'm a good liar.
I'm a very good liar,
but you, you're better.
You fooled her.
Hell, you fooled all of us
for what, 20 years?
Wait,
does Mark know
that his dad's a murderer?
Does he know?
No?
Well, what's he gonna do
when he finds out, huh?
This is pointless.
You can't stop me.
Yeah, you're right.
I can't,
but I can do the same thing
I've been doing
since I figured out you were
a lying piece of shit.
I can buy us a little more time.
[teleporter whooshes,
rocks crumbling]
[grunts]
[impacts thud]
-[cyborg shrieks]
-Ha!
[shrieking]
[Nolan grunts]
[seething]
[groaning]
[Nolan roars]
[groans in pain]
[Nolan yelps]
[screams]
[growling]
[Nolan screams]
[Debbie] What are those things?
Dead soldiers.
Serving their country
one last time
thanks to that monster
over there.
[mumbling]
Shut it!
I feel dirty
even talking to you.
[mumbles petulantly]
[cyborgs shrieking]
[Nolan grunts]
[shrieking]
[grunts]
[shrieks]
[grunts with effort]
[body rending and breaking]
[all gasping in horror]
[crunch]
[gasps]
Bring 'em over here,
bring 'em over here right now.
Teleport me to Invincible
and Eve's location.
Once they get these strapped on,
you bring us home.
Sir,
Eve and Invincible
are back on the move.
Intercept in four minutes.
Shit.
[grunts, blood splashing]
[gasps]
[roars]
[annoyed grumble]
Shit!
[horrified gasps and retching]
[groans]
Get him out of here...
...and get Hail Mary
out of the icebox...
[gasps of shock]
...and feed her this!
What a dick.
You want revenge?
Quit complaining
and finish the build.
I'm almost done here.
[charging defibrillator]
It's charged.
I built it exactly
to the schematics.
Good.
How do we know he'll revive?
Cecil couldn't bring him back.
Cecil's an idiot.
[staples pop free]
He's not called The Immortal
for nothing.
I'll get the collar.
[teleporter whoosh]
[grunts]
[roars]
[Nolan grunts, beast bellows]
You must be desperate.
I beat this thing already.
[bellowing]
[Cecil's voice, from drone]
Sure...
but we removed its pain center,
and juiced it up
with every drug, enhancement,
and upgrade we had.
Plus, all that
really pissed it off,
and it blames you.
Good luck.
[bellowing roar]
There are two news helicopters
moving in on Omni-Man's fight.
[news report] Omni-Man
appears to be fighting
the same creature he battled
in the sea of Japan
over half a year ago.
We need to go help.
Keep your asses parked
until I tell you
to unpark them.
If this all goes south,
you're our last hope
against Omni-Man.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Did he just say
we're his last hope
"against" Omni-Man?
Yeah, he did.
Oh, fuck.
I'm pretty sure
that's what happened
to the last
"last hope against Omni-Man."
[beast snarls]
[Nolan roars]
That should buy us
five minutes or so.
Teleport me
to Invincible's location.
Can't, sir.
Hail Mary was so big,
she burnt out the teleporter.
Well, goddammit, get it working,
or we're all dead.
Where do you think
he's coming next?
[grunting]
[groaning]
Mark's with Eve again.
Call her phone.
[snaps fingers]
Took you long enough.
I'm not here to help.
Just here to make sure
you don't get hurt.
Well, then
you shouldn't have come.
Jesus, Mark,
you sound just like my--
Dad!
[groans weakly]
[beast bellows]
[Mark grunts]
[cell phone rings]
[Debbie] Eve!
It's Mark's mom.
I need to talk to him!
You just missed him.
What's going on?
Dad!
You okay?
Mark?
You mean Invincible.
It's about time
we did a team-up.
[bellowing roar]
Blech!
Come on!
But I need to help them!
[Cecil] Do not do that.
[groaning]
[Cecil] Get to Guardians HQ.
What? Cecil!
Listen to me and do what I say.
[bellowing]
[gasps]
Call that thing off, Cecil.
[groans]
Call it off!
Mark's in there.
[groans]
I can't do that, Debbie.
Why not?
Because I can't.
Nolan killed the Guardians,
he killed Donald.
He's shrugged off
everything I've thrown at him,
and now I don't know
if Mark is with his father,
or against him.
So I can't call off
the one thing
that might stop them both.
This is why
I have always hated you.
[sighs]
That's why I hate me, too.
What now?
I don't know.
He should just be alive.
He's not.
You're so observant.
[roars, thumping]
What are you doing?
Even Frankenstein
needed an extra kick
to come to life.
One, he's not Frankenstein.
Two, it was lightning,
and not whatever you're doing,
and three, that was only
in the movie version.
I know,
but this also feels good.
Wake up, you useless
murdered idiot!
[Mauler's voice echoes]
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
[thumps pulsing]
[echoes of sword battle]
[grunts]
[echoes of audience clapping]
[gasps]
[roaring]
Activate the collar.
Where is he?
[beeps device]
[roars]
Immortal,
you're going to destroy Robot
and the new Guardians
of the Globe for us.
[roaring]
[seething with rage]
-Uh-oh.
-Where's Omni-man?
Where is he?
[Immortal roaring in fury]
Robot gave us bad schematics.
No kidding.
[beast bellows]
H'a!
[grunting with effort]
Didn't you fight
this thing before?
Yeah, but it's tougher now.
Cecil sent it after me.
Cecil?
Why would he do that?
There's so much
you don't know, Mark.
What?
Uh, okay.
Uh, maybe you can fill me in
after we've taken care
of tentacles here?
[beast bellowing]
Mark?
Sir!
What?
There's a new contact
approaching Omni-Man
and Invincible.
Mach three.
Goddammit,
I told Eve to stay away.
It's not Atom Eve.
[distant roar of fury]
Omni-Man!
You bastard!
[roaring]
[roaring and grunting]
[newscaster]
I'm having a hard time
believing what I'm seeing
here, folks,
but the Immortal,
or someone
who appears to be him,
has suddenly attacked Omni-Man.
As you all know,
the Immortal was murdered
eight months ago,
along with the other members
of the original
Guardians of the Globe.
The killer was never caught.
Murderer!
We trusted you!
You betrayed us!
You should've stayed dead.
[tentacle beast bellowing]
Dad?
[snarling]
[grunting, blows pounding]
[groans]
[Immortal roaring]
[bellowing]
[grunts]
[volts crackle, beast screams]
[roaring]
[impact thunders]
I'll kill you!
H'a!
[fist pops, Immortal gurgles]
[vomits]
[tense silence]
[wheezing]
[screaming]
[groans of rage and pain]
H'a!
[growls]
Dad?
Mark...
We need to talk.