[Donald]
We wanted Nolan off planet
so we could investigate him
for the murders
without arousing his suspicion.
What does sending Mark away
get us?
A chance to see
what this kid can do.
More importantly,
if his heart's
in the right place.
Who the hell are you?
Where are you going?
You know, it's desert-y.
[Amber] You don't know
where you're going.
Go, go, go, go, go!
[Mark] Please don't lose
interest in me while I'm gone.
Hey, Cecil.
You missed a spot?
Left that one there
as a reminder,
and when you prove yourselves
worthy of the heroes
who came before you,
it will get cleaned off.
[Damien Darkblood]
You murdered seven people.
Wife already suspects.
[Donald] Dominari...
[Cecil]
You didn't listen to me
when I told you
to drop the goddamn case.
[Nolan] Nothing to worry about.
Everything's fine.
[din of city traffic]
[yawns]
[lighter snaps open]
[flint clicks]
[flint clicking]
Huh?
[clicking safety switches]
["Make Way For the King"
by Ohana Bam plays]
♪ They say I walk like a king ♪
♪ Talk like a king ♪
♪ You can ask around
they'll say the same thing ♪
♪ They chasing the fame ♪
♪ They all want the name ♪
♪ But they ain't got ♪
♪ What's running through
these veins ♪
♪ Say I walk like a king ♪
♪ Talk like a king ♪
♪ You can ask around
they'll say the same thing ♪
♪ They're chasing the fame... ♪
[Titan roaring]
[gunfire crackling]
[heavy crash]
♪ ...Make way for the king ♪
[♪♪♪]
Kill him!
[continuous gunfire]
[stone rumbling]
My turn.
♪ What can I say
I got go genes... ♪
[zoom]
[screams]
[crashing]
[gasps]
♪ ...Everybody can be.. ♪
[grunts, gunfire]
[screams]
[gunfire]
[shots blasting]
[grunts]
[gunfire]
[roars]
-[squelch]
-[gasps]
[gunfire]
[screams]
♪ ...Big cars, big man
big plan... ♪
[blow thuds]
-[weapon cocks]
-[roars]
-♪ Look at me now... ♪
-What the fuck?
♪ Can't hold me down... ♪
[roars]
[shots blast]
[thud]
[groans]
[shot blasts]
[man] Get out of here!
Get out of here! Come on!
[gunfire]
[groaning with effort]
[grunts]
Ooh.
Tell Mr. Liu,
next time I find him
on our turf,
I won't be so gentle.
[bones crack]
[body slumps]
That message was for you.
Don't be stupid, kid.
I'm cutting you a break--
[groans in pain]
[stone rumbling]
[grunting]
Go.
Oh, shit...
[blaster firing,
laughs gleefully]
This time, I'm ready!
[screams, car crunching]
I surrender--
Yo, roll that back.
Oh, this new guy's dope.
[groans]
[whoosh, running steps]
Hey.
[chuckles] Yes,
I'm 20 minutes late,
but there's no way
you're gonna be mad at me.
And how do you figure that?
Because I brought you
Japanese cheesecake.
You went
all the way across town
to get cheesecake--
Yup.
--to make up for being late,
because you went across town
to get cheesecake?
Is that crazy?
Yeah, it kind of is.
I mean, I could take it back,
but that'll probably just
make me even more late--
[chuckles]
Hey!
What'd we ever
do to you?
Kevin, shut up.
Leave it alone.
[grumbles]
[crowd gasps, wincing]
There's a place
on Third and Parkland.
They'll put you up
for a few weeks.
[grunts]
[crashing]
-You're welcome!
-[crowd cheering]
Just trying to keep
the city safe.
Behind you!
What? Oh, crap.
[building crumbling]
[child screams]
Hi.
Don't be scared.
I got this,
but, uh, I guess,
get your stuff?
Sorry about your apartment.
[Mr. Sayer]
45 minutes late!
It won't happen again,
Mr. Sayer.
But it has, Grayson.
You've been late 12 times
in the past three months.
I'm sorry,
but I'm docking
your shifts.
[chuckles]
You know what?
Don't bother.
I quit.
What!
[Sam] Mr. Sayer? There's a rat
in the mayonnaise again.
Do I look like I care, Sam?
[whoosh]
Grayson?
[Gary] I'll have the cash
tomorrow, I swear!
Tell your boss
I need more time!
There isn't
any more time, Gary.
Take it all.
Take everything I got.
[grumbles]
[grunts] Oof!
Two days.
After that,
you're painting sidewalk.
Oh, God!
[Mark shouts]
The Gravity Bomb, where is it?
I'll never tell!
[gasping in fear]
[sighs]
Now what?
Mark, you have to scare him.
Make him think
you'll actually drop him.
I can hear you!
I don't know,
that seems mean.
All right here,
I'll show you.
[screams]
-Whoa!
-There, see?
Now he'll tell me
everything.
Okay, but you're
gonna catch him, right?
Yeah.
In a second.
[panting]
Crap.
Uh, Principal Winslow.
Uh... hi.
Mr. Grayson.
If you're planning
to attend college,
we need to have
a conversation
about your recent...
attendance issues.
Uh, what if I'm not planning
to attend college?
[alarms wailing]
[hydraulic motors whir]
Freeze!
Your lives worth
minimum wage?
Or do you wanna fire
your guns in the air,
say you tried your best,
and we all walk away happy,
and alive?
[gunfire rattling]
[Mark, in text]
"Hey, can't make it tonight.
Just got hit by something."
[opponent grunts]
[Amber, in text]
"You're standing me up?
You tread on dangerous ground,
my friend."
[Mark, in text]
"It'll be worth the wait
to see me
on my best behavior."
[pipe clangs]
[Amber, in text]
"Do not miss dinner
with my mom on Thursday
if you value everything
you hold dear, Mark Grayson."
[Mark, in text]
"Not for the end of the world."
[crashing]
Seriously?
Not even scratched?
Not bad for a guy
with gravel
for fingers.
[circuits crackle]
[energy surging]
[moans] Oh... yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that's...
that's nice.
That works nicely.
[Titan] That's the last of it.
Paid in full.
I'm done.
Mm... nah.
Nah?
See, Titan,
your problem
is you're too useful.
You get shit done.
You take bullets like a champ,
and don't even whine about it,
unlike someone else
in the room.
It was
one fucking time.
-I said--
-Shut the hell up!
Yeah, yeah, sometimes,
you let people live
when they need to die,
but, man, you make an impact.
If you didn't just finish
paying off your debt,
we'd be talking bonus time.
I don't need
your money anymore.
Sure, you do.
Come on, like
you're gonna go clean?
Work the fry-station
at Burger-Mart?
That ship
has sailed, amigo.
This is your life now.
This is what you do.
No, it's not.
You're a walking
pile of rocks.
You break heads.
That's it.
That's all.
Own it already.
See, I know you're gonna
keep working for me.
The question is,
how painful do you
want it to be?
-[stone rumbling]
-What are you doing?
[laughs]
You think you can just
punch your way out of this?
I know where
your family lives,
and that means
you work for me
until I say
you're fucking done!
-[roars]
-Yeah, see?
See!
Impressive shit
like that
is exactly why
I'm never
letting you go!
Plus, now you gotta
pay for the desk, too.
This was imported
Italian maple.
[grumbles]
[♪♪♪]
[sighs in relief]
Now just
throw it back into space.
[gasping wearily]
[grunts]
[roars]
How does it feel
to save the world?
Or at least the country?
By the way,
that was a small one.
That was a small one?
Yeah, you should've
seen the asteroid
I diverted a few years ago.
The size of Texas.
-[text alert beeps]
-Aw, crap.
I gotta run, Dad.
Hey, whatever that is,
your training
is more important.
Big picture, right?
I know, but it's Amber.
Mark, we talked about this.
[groans] Dad...
[sighs indulgently]
This one time, okay?
Yes!
[knocking on door]
I know I'm a little late...
I brought dessert.
[groans] Ugh.
Okay, that's fair.
You were right.
Your mom's
a great cook.
You should've
told her that yourself.
During dinner.
Two hours ago.
I tried to text you--
Am I important
to you, Mark?
Uh... yeah.
Of course.
Well, it really
doesn't feel like it.
Half the time
we make plans,
you're late,
or you cancel,
or you just don't show,
and your excuses suck.
Hold on--
But then you pick up
the sushi I like,
or you leave a note
in my locker,
or you surprise me after class,
and you're not a bad kisser,
but that doesn't make it okay
if you keep doing it,
and tonight was just definitely
not okay.
This was three months.
This was meeting my mom.
It's just...
I have these
family responsibilities.
I help my dad with work.
It's hard making it all fit.
Sure. That's fine.
Then make that choice,
but then this?
I'm not doing this anymore.
I've been down
this road before,
and once was enough.
Hold on--
Why?
Because...
I'm, uh...
You're what?
I'm...
I'm gonna do better.
I promise.
Prove it.
[sighs]
[smash]
[whoosh]
[gasps]
[cell phone rings]
[beeps on]
Hey, Dad.
Mark,
I'm watching the Elephant
rob a store downtown.
He'd be perfect practice
for you.
I'm not really in the mood--
Mark...
[Elephant trumpeting]
Okay. I'm coming.
That's my boy.
[beeps off]
[dishes clatter distantly]
[TV show plays]
Did somebody ask
for butterscotch ripple?
Daddy!
Mommy, he got my text!
Good.
Means we still have service.
We're not out, are we?
Nessa, it's not that simple.
[Nessa sighs]
Don't.
[man] Get the fuck out of here!
Get your stupid...
I wanna sit with you.
Wait, baby.
Let me help.
Daddy look,
a superhero!
Is he a good guy?
That's what people say.
Are you a good guy?
I...
What's his name?
Him?
He calls himself--
[shivers] Brr...
[exhales]
Seven dead.
One Alive.
Your husband.
[Nolan] Hey, Debbie--
Jesus!
What was the name
of that place in Bordeaux?
The one with the chocolate
pastry thingies?
Uh, the...
Éclair d'André?
That's it!
Thanks, sweetie.
[door locks]
Hey, I need
my costume back.
I don't care
how torn up it is.
It's classified,
and I want it back.
Go get it.
Now.
I don't need to tell you
when I break up with someone.
The only, and I mean
only reason
I agreed to you
being a superhero
was because Rex was there
to take care of you.
I can take care
of myself.
Your father only means
that we liked Rex
very much,
and we felt good
that he was keeping you safe.
But now that you're not even
part of a team...
Rex cheated on me!
Teen Team broke up.
They're both over.
It happens.
-Forgive him.
-What?
All guys make mistakes!
Don't be a--
You're an 18-year-old girl.
You can't do
this hero bullshit on your own.
You shouldn't be
doing it at all.
One, I can do anything
I want on my own.
-Literally!
-[energy crackling]
I can rearrange atoms
on a molecular level
like it's easy,
and two,
I'm not even sure
I want to do this anymore!
Good!
It's about time.
That includes
this stupid family!
[energy crackling]
Samantha!
Don't you leave
that door there!
["Alive" by Battle Tapes plays]
[Mark] Whoo-hoo!
[sighs]
Huh?
[grunts]
♪ Been sailing seas
of the spoiled and the rotten ♪
♪ Been throwing over board
the once forgotten ♪
♪ Things you never think about
when thinking's such a bore ♪
[♪♪♪]
Huh?
[chuckles]
You missed a few letters.
Paint costs money
and you got a long-ass name.
Oh, you're that guy I stopped
from robbing a bank
a few months ago.
My name's Titan.
Oh... you're--
you're out for revenge.
Fine, let's do this.
I didn't call you
here to fight.
Because I'd win?
You got lucky.
Sure, I did.
[grumbles]
I called you here
because I need your help.
[laughs]
Why would I help you?
You're a criminal.
You don't even know
what that word means.
Uh, pretty sure I do.
No, you don't.
I'm not a criminal,
I just owed one money,
and now
I can't get out.
So?
So aren't you a hero?
Helping people
and taking down
bad guys?
Yeah...
So help me take down my boss.
They don't get
any worse than him.
Who's your boss?
Machine Head.
That's not a real name.
Huh.
Of course, you haven't
heard of him.
You're a rich kid
from the suburbs.
What? No, I'm--
You don't know!
Come on, man.
Machine Head runs this city.
If it's illegal
and it makes money,
it's his,
and when people need to die
to keep it that way,
he's got muscle like me
to take care of it.
Yeah, I'm more like
a big picture superhero.
Saving the planet,
stuff like that.
Why don't you give, uh,
Fight Force a call?
Sure, man,
just fly away.
Forget about
everyone else down here.
Let me show you
what you don't see
from up there.
What, like, right now?
You got somewhere to be?
This is some bullshit.
It's not a party
for me either, man.
[Titan] Machine Head
owns the trash company,
uses it to ferry drugs
to stash houses
all over the city.
Machine Head owns
this whole block.
He pays off inspectors
so he doesn't have to fix shit,
then burns them
for insurance money.
If anyone's inside
at the time,
too bad.
[text buttons tapping]
Which one's
Machine Head?
Kidding.
I'm kidding.
[Machine Head]
Isotope, let's go.
[energy buzzes]
What the hell was that?
His pet.
You help me take down
Machine Head,
you help real people
with real lives.
Think about that
next time you're fighting
some stupid elephant-man
or whatever.
Why did you borrow money
from Machine Head anyway?
[little girl giggles]
It wasn't for me.
Daddy!
[woman and girl gasp]
[Mark] I know I can take
Machine Head.
He's just a criminal
with a... special head,
but he does have
this right-hand man--
uh, Iso...
Isotope or something,
I don't know--
who can teleport him away
if I'm not careful.
Mom, can you pass
the potatoes, please?
Mom?
Sorry.
I dunno.
Do you think I should
help this Titan guy out?
You'd be making
a huge mistake.
What? Why?
Because he's using you.
I'm not an idiot, Dad.
I know when someone's lying.
Titan never wanted to be
a criminal in the first place.
He has a family.
I think his daughter's sick.
Even if that was true,
you're a Viltrumite, okay?
You fought off
an alien invasion,
saved the country
from an asteroid.
This is beneath you.
Mom?
I know that sometimes
people aren't
who they appear to be.
Exactly.
Listen to your mother.
You help this guy,
you're gonna learn
a very painful lesson.
But I also know
that helping someone
is never beneath you.
[Mark] I'm gonna sleep on this.
[Nolan] Fine.
["I Can Get It Myself"
by Aceyalone plays]
♪ Yeah... ♪
[Rex Splode]
Whoo! Fuck, yeah!
That's the last time
the Lizard League turns people
into snakes in my town!
[laughs]
You better
believe it, baby.
Who wants a beer?
[Robot] There are
no alcoholic beverages
in Guardian Headquarters.
There "were"
no alcoholic beverages
in Guardian Headquarters.
First thing I fixed
in this dump.
Had to throw out
whatever scanner
or computer
was in that spot, though.
[gasps in mock horror]
Oh, no!
I hope that wasn't
your girlfriend, Robot!
Up top.
[laughter]
♪ Told 'em I can,
I can get it myself... ♪
♪ The reverend and the priest ♪
♪ Both tried to get
my sins released... ♪
I'm 25.
♪ ...To give me the blessing
to kill the beast ♪
♪ I told 'em I can
I can get it myself... ♪
Nothing like
an ice-cold brew
after you've crawled through
someone's inner ear--
[high frequency
shatters glass]
Dude! What the hell?
Two dozen civilians
are in the hospital
right now
because we fought like
six individual assholes
instead of a team.
Pull up the fight.
[trill of display activating]
[display beeps]
You see this, Rex?
This right here?
I know what a bus looks like.
This is where you messed up,
you and Monster Girl.
Both so caught up
in your own little prize fights
that you let this entire bus
of civilians crash.
[tires screech]
[crashing]
[display beeps]
It had kids on it, man.
What were we
supposed to do?
You pop the tires on the bus,
blow that concrete to gravel
to slow it down,
so Monster Girl can stop it
and save lives!
That is what
you were supposed to do!
[crowd screaming in panic]
Dupli-Kate,
next time
we're in this situation,
I want you to think
about containment.
If you had cloned the perimeter
around King Lizard here,
you could've held him back
while Shrinking Rae
took care of his snake gun,
or whatever the hell
he called it.
"Snake-erator."
He called it
his snake-erator.
No!
Forget this.
We did our best,
and we won.
So whatever.
You don't even
have powers, old man.
Say that
one more time, son.
Why?
Forget your hearing aid,
Grandpa?
Okay, okay.
Stop.
He's not wrong, Rex.
Fuck this!
Good debrief, everyone.
As usual,
I'll be the only person
who actually sacrificed
something,
since I'm now
a week younger
than I was yesterday.
Can you believe these punks?
Some of them.
Why would you tell Mark
that saving lives
is beneath him?
Other people save lives.
Mark saves millions.
He needs to think big,
and you're not helping.
I'm not helping?
You don't understand
the choices we have to make.
You're not a superhero.
When you first came here,
you didn't know anything,
about humans,
or our society,
or what was important to us.
And?
I taught you all that.
I showed you
how to be a hero, here,
and, suddenly, you think
I can't do that for Mark?
That's not what I meant.
I just...
I think Mark
is putting his trust
in someone he shouldn't,
instead of listening to me--
to us,
even when we disagree.
He's only been a hero
for a few months.
He thinks he knows
everything.
I just don't want him
to make a choice
he'll regret.
Neither do I.
[Nolan] This is all going
so quickly.
I didn't think
it'd be this difficult.
[school bell rings]
Well, that sucked.
This superhero thing
is destroying my GPA.
Like you'll ever need
to find Mongolia on a map.
I know, right?
No, you do need
to know that.
I'm not kidding,
it's really important
that you can find places
from the air.
Oh, yeah.
[chuckles] Right.
You okay, Eve?
You look... down.
You ever read about
those kids
who get kicked out
of the house at 16,
and wish it was you?
Uh... no.
Not really.
Do you want to talk about it?
Yes. No.
I don't know.
I-I just don't know
what I'm doing anymore.
[Amber] Mark!
Hey, you.
Slow down, tiger,
you're still
on my shit list.
You're coming
tonight, right?
Hey, Eve.
Of course, I'm coming.
Do not stand me up
on this, okay?
It won't only be me
counting on you this time.
Mark volunteered
to help me
at the Beckwell
Community Center downtown.
We do dinners twice a week
for anyone who's hungry.
I'm impressed.
[Amber] Do not be.
He owes me.
Beckwell's like
my second home.
I used to hang there
after school
till my mom
was done working.
Changed my life.
It's on Third Street, right?
Low brick building?
Yeah. 7:00 p.m.
-[alarm beeps]
-Oh, man, gotta run.
I told my mom I'd help
with an open house.
I'll see you there.
Bye, Eve!
[Amber] You wanna come tonight?
We could use the help.
Mm. I wish I could, but...
Too busy saving the world?
Hmm.
Not anymore, actually.
No excuse then.
You and Mark
are pretty close.
Has he been acting
weird lately?
What do you mean?
He's late,
all the time,
or doesn't show,
and then lies about why.
At least I think he's lying.
I don't know if I can
deal with it much longer.
Guys are dicks...
but Mark's one
of the good ones.
Yeah, his time management
is awful,
but he's super into you.
You're all he talks about.
Really? Hmm.
Well, thanks for that.
See you tonight?
Yeah.
[Titan] The only place
we're guaranteed
to find Machine Head
is 60 stories up.
The room is lined with windows,
but they're bomb-proofed
with something.
There's a whole team
of ex-military assholes
patrolling the place,
packing the latest shit, too.
[Mark]
Which is why you need me, hmm?
I'm tough,
but I'm not stupid.
Can't the teleporter guy
just pull
Machine Head out
once we get close?
I took care of Isotope.
How?
He's got a girl he sees
a couple of times a week.
I paid her extra
to keep him there
all evening.
What?
Oh... okay.
So we break
into the penthouse
and grab Machine Head.
Then what?
Don't you got friends
who can keep a guy
like him off the street?
I could take him
to the Global Defense Agency.
See?
Doin' good already, hero.
That was your daughter,
back at Beckwell
Community Center, right?
What's her name?
Fiona.
You guys go there often?
It's her second home.
Okay, I'm in,
but we have to make it quick.
I've got plans later tonight.
[energy crackles]
[snoring]
[pod hisses open]
Huh?
I almost forgot
how good I look.
[♪♪♪]
[circuits crackling]
[groaning]
[power whines down]
[♪♪♪]
[grunts and chuckles]
Welcome to the world
of the living, clone.
[♪♪♪]
Don't start.
I'm the original.
[chuckles]
So the process
was a success.
[Robot] I'll never understand
why you do that.
[gasps]
[roaring]
[grunts]
[gas hissing]
Stop, please.
I'm not here to fight.
[roars]
Not the replication
chamber, idiot!
As I was trying to say,
I need your expertise
in tissue growth
and DNA replication.
I'll make it
worth your while.
[sighs heavily]
[line ringing]
Hi, honey.
If you have a sec,
could you pick up
a few things for dinner?
Well, I was thinking
some tagliatelle
from that restaurant in Rome,
and maybe that wine
from Provence,
the rosé.
Yeah.
Thanks, sweetie.
Love you.
[beeps call off]
[sighs]
[sonic boom]
[♪♪♪]
What am I doing?
[gasps]
[timer beeps]
[screen door slides open]
What the...?
[shattering]
[grunts]
[splintering]
Machine Head!
[Mark] Get up.
We're taking you in.
Hey!
[slamming]
It's over.
You're way
out of your league.
Carry the two...
Oh, hello, Invincible.
Titan.
Boss.
[Machine Head] You're right.
You're so strong,
and tough,
and you...
you, you fly all over
the goddamn place.
It's amazing.
Uh... thanks?
You know a lot about me.
I also knew
exactly when
you and this giant
pile of shit
would walk in here
and ruin my doors.
Also, Italian maple,
by the way!
No way you saw
this coming--
Aw, is that
what you think?
See, this is what happens
when your head's a fuckin' rock.
You said you took
care of him.
I know what I said.
This little upgrade
shows me all kinds
of possibilities,
which is how I know
it's not worth
explaining to you two morons
what quantum probabilities are,
but it doesn't matter,
because, like I said,
Invincible's right,
I'm out of my league.
Except...
I've got money!
[electricity crackles]
[snarling]
Oh, shit.
[laughing]
You have no idea, kid.
[Eve] Amber?
Hey! Eve!
You made it.
Come on,
I'll show you around.
Chicken.
Mashed potatoes.
Salad.
Minestrone on the stove,
but we'll need another pot soon.
It's nothing fancy,
but it's healthy.
Hey, my parents cook
exclusively
with a microwave.
This looks like a dream.
Mark here yet?
That boy's got
about 15 minutes
until his ass
is on the curb,
permanently.
You look like you're good
at chopping things.
How'd you know?
[distant grunts and blows]
[lightning zaps]
[grunts]
[mighty snarl]
[mace clanks]
[shouts]
Ah!
[groans]
[debris tumbling]
[gasping]
[grunts with effort]
[ceiling crumbles]
[Mark screams]
[grunts in pain] Oof!
[Machine Head]
I'm gonna grind you up
and use you
to pave my driveway.
[screaming]
[screams]
[lenses shatter]
[groaning in pain]
No!
[gasping]
[screams in rage]
[Mark]
You guys are fucking dead!
[shouts explosively]
[roaring]
[squelching]
Who's next?
[crunch]
Hello, boy.
[groans]
[smashing]
[blows thud wetly]
[Mark groans]
Wow!
Ten out of ten!
You guys, you guys
are worth every cent--
Wait.
Wait, I'm getting
something here.
What?
Cecil got an anonymous call.
[team grunts in readiness]
We'll take it
from here.
[moaning]
[roaring]
[groans]
[grunts]
[muffled explosions]
[rapid gunfire]
[electric bolts zap]
[shouts battle cry]
[wall crumbling]
Murder!
These!
Assholes!
[snarling]
[screaming]
Dupli-Kate,
Monster Girl
is in trouble.
[shouting]
[splashing]
[thuds, smashing]
[shouts in distress]
[circuits crackle]
[mace slams]
[hollow metal clank]
Huh?
[yelps]
[gasps]
[Battle Beast] I was promised
this world offered
worthy opponents!
[gasping in fear]
[foot crunching]
But, oh,
how you disappoint.
Killing you
is an act of mercy.
[circuits crackle]
[roaring]
[Black Samson] Hey, asshole!
[groans]
[roars]
[screams]
[scream fades, echoing]
[splashing]
[groans]
[bellowing]
Invincible!
[Robot] Black Samson, retreat!
[roaring]
-[hand bones crunch]
-[screams]
[bones crunching,
Samson screams]
[groans]
[wet thudding]
[electricity zaps]
[groaning in pain]
[roaring]
[punches smash and crunch]
Pathetic child.
[smashing]
[moaning]
[gasps, splashing]]
[snarling]
[squelching]
[Robot screams] No!
[Battle Beast shouts]
[chuckles smugly]
You guys just messed up.
Indeed.
Big time.
[Battle Beast growls]
[rocks crack, echoing]
[grunting with effort]
[grunting]
[grunts]
[explosions]
[hydraulic motors whirr]
[grunting and blasting]
[lava squelching]
[roars]
[bolts zapping]
[energy surging]
[explosion shattering]
[explosions bang]
[roars]
[choking]
Pathetic.
This battle is beneath me.
[bodies slump]
There is no honor
in killing insects.
[gasps in horror]
No...
No, no, no.
This was
an unexpected possibility.
Isotope, let's go.
Isotope!
[punch clanks]
[groaning]
Sorry, kid.
Didn't mean for it
to end this way,
but I gotta take care of mine.
I hope you make it.
The veggies are nice
and soft tonight, Rose.
I made sure of it.
Aw, thanks, Amber.
Kurt, you want to find me
in the kitchen later?
I've got that book
we were talking about.
That be great, thanks.
What?
I can barely remember
my English class,
and you know
everyone here by name.
Make the world
you wanna live in, right?
Right.
I thought Mark
would be here tonight.
I really did.
[gasping]
[paramedic]
He's losing too much blood.
Get pressure on that wound.
Quick! Check his pupils.
[Robot] She's fibrillating.
Step back.
[whine of paddles charging]
[Cecil] Jesus fucking Christ.
Are we gonna lose him?
It's a possibility, sir.
No. We need him.
Do whatever it takes.
Get a sample to the lab,
just in case.
Huh?
[stun bolt blasts]
[powering down,
casing hisses]
[paramedic] He's losing
way too much blood.
[Mark whispers] ...Dad?
[monitors beeping rapidly]
We're losing him!
[cell phone rings]
I gotta take this.
[gasps]
[beeps phone off]
Amber, I'm sorry.
I... I have to go.
What's wrong?
Was that Mark?
[Robot]
It's okay, I'm here.
I'll fix you.
I know it's hard
to love someone
when they don't seem
to love you back,
but Mark loves you.
He'd be here if he could.
[♪♪♪]
[Isotope] Wow...
[chuckles]
I gotta hand it to you, boss.
Whatever you told that kid
to get him on your side,
it fuckin'--
I told him the truth.
I'm gonna make this city better
for a lot of people...
[elevator dings]
...but some people
come first.
Daddy!
Mm...
Is this our new house?
♪ Make way for the king... ♪
[♪♪♪]
♪ Make way for the kingdom ♪
♪ King me, checkmate... ♪
♪ This chess, not checkers ♪
♪ What can I say... ♪
[beeping code]
[panel beeps]
Any progress?
[exhales ruefully]
Jesus, that bad?
We've tried everything.
Drugs, viruses,
bacteria, prions,
even nanobots and radioactives.
Viltrumite cells
don't give a damn.
They just won't die.
Well, keep trying.
I got a feeling
blood's still the answer.