[♪♪♪]
[fighter jets overhead]
[sonic boom]
I've fought the unimaginable
in defense of this world.
I've battled alien tyrants,
defeated nightmares
from the deep.
Gone toe to toe
with ancient gods...
but no matter what threat
I faced,
I knew I wasn't facing it alone.
Darkwing.
Aquarus.
War Woman.
Green Ghost.
Red Rush.
Martian Man.
Immortal.
The Guardians of the Globe.
Today, we have lost titans,
protectors,
heroes,
and we are left to wonder...
who will save us now?
I will,
and so will others like me.
New heroes answering the call.
New champions
ready to risk everything
to keep this planet safe.
All inspired
by these great souls
who came before us.
You will have moments of doubt,
of fear,
of uncertainty,
but in those moments,
have faith...
and look to the sky.
[woman sobbing]
[Mark] We seriously
have to put everyone
through this again?
The big one's for show,
but the public can't know
where the actual bodies
are buried.
Souvenir hunters.
Jesus.
[Nolan] I was never
a Guardian of the Globe,
but it was the Guardians
who welcomed me
when I first arrived
on this planet.
They were my mentors.
My comrades.
My friends.
They knew the reality
of this life.
Martian Man was exiled
from his own people.
War Woman
was from a different age.
Darkwing...
[chuckles ruefully]
[clears throat]
Well, Darkwing made
his own kind of solitude.
It was a rare, lucky few of us
who found someone
who understood our path,
even rarer
if they accepted it.
I hope they will rest in peace,
but at least
they will rest together.
[woman sobbing]
Get your hands off me!
[screams in anguish]
Olga, please, calm down.
You wouldn't even
let me see him.
Josef is finally standing still,
and I still can't see him!
I'd better...
Yeah.
You okay?
Me? I... I dunno.
It just doesn't seem real.
That could have been my mom,
putting my dad
in one of those holes,
or me.
If this could happen
to the Guardians of the Globe,
it means that none of us are...
[Olga sobbing]
[huffs]
This is a private ceremony,
Darkblood.
[grumbles]
Never get invited.
Show up anyway.
What do you want?
Same as you.
Discover clues.
Catch killer.
Bring to justice.
And buy yourself
a few more years out of hell.
Don't pretend you do this
because you care.
You just don't want to go home.
Maybe one day, you'll know why.
I already told Cecil
everything I know.
Saw nothing.
Heard nothing.
Attacked in darkness.
Left for dead.
Are you insinuating something?
[grumbles]
Didn't mean to offend.
Nuance of human conversation
difficult for me.
If you remember something...
[Nolan] I'll call you.
[Olga] Josef...
[Debbie]
Let's get you in a car, Olga.
[Cecil] Robot!
You know, for a bunch
of computer code,
you run a mean superhero team.
You really saved our bacon
with those Flaxans.
[Robot] Thank you, Cecil.
That means a lot
coming from you.
I know you've always
been independent,
but I want you
to come work for the GDA,
and build me
a new Guardians of the Globe.
Now, you'll pick the team,
you'll be in charge.
The only person
that you will answer to is me.
Forgive me,
but would Omni-Man
not be the natural choice?
Sure.
Except it's never gonna happen.
I've tried for a decade
to make him
an official Guardian.
He helps out, yeah,
but he's never taken orders,
not from me, anyway.
Then I don't know
what to say...
Easy.
Say you'll do it.
[door closes]
I'm feeling pizza.
I can be to Naples and back
before the cheese
stops bubbling.
Honey,
let the delivery guy
do it tonight.
Sure.
I've battled alien tyrants,
defeated nightmares
from the deep,
gone toe to toe...
[click]
You will have moments
of doubt...
[click]
We are left to wonder...
-Mark...
-Who will save us now?
Why don't you call William?
And do what?
Hang out?
Go buy comic books?
After this?
[Nolan] Hey...
Watch the tone.
[Debbie] It's okay.
It's not.
This is new, I get it,
but you need
to keep that separate.
What happens out there,
the mistakes,
even the victories,
you can't bring it home.
Okay?
Can I go to my room?
[sighs] Sure.
Hey, we'll do some more
training tomorrow, okay?
Just you and me.
What?
We just came from
your friends' funeral.
Co-workers.
And you're talking about pizza,
and telling Mark
not to feel anything?
This is the life.
Mark has to learn that.
What if Mark and I
were burying you today?
I'm not so easy to kill.
Yeah, well, I'm sure that's
what Red Rush told Olga.
Hey, he could run fast, okay?
It's not exactly one of
your premier superpowers.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean that,
but Mark and I can do
more good out there
than sulking in here.
[Debbie, on hidden microphone]
Just remember
that Mark's a 17-year-old boy.
They break more easily
than you think,
and I don't want
a broken family...
[♪♪♪]
[music playing quietly]
[cell phone rings]
Hello?
Hey, it's, uh, it's Mark.
Grays-Grayson.
Mark Grayson.
Who?
Mark?
From school?
[laughter]
I know.
I'm just messing with you.
Oh, god, you thought
I was serious.
Oh, no, no, I...
I got it.
I was wondering
if you were going to call.
Don't you mean "when"?
Nah, I can think up
a few reasons for "if".
I came on too strong.
You've got a girlfriend.
You're lame,
and you don't like chicks
who kick assholes in the balls
when they threaten you...
Uh...
You're terrified of me,
aren't you?
No!
I think you're amazing.
That's why I'm calling
to tell you that.
I mean....
that's not why I'm calling.
Not that that's not true.
[sighing] Ah...
Sorry.
It's been a weird day.
Sounds like it.
You wanna start again?
Hey, handsome Mark Grayson?
What's going on?
I was thinking,
finals are coming up,
and we're both in Ms. Walker's
Global Issues class.
Maybe we can go over
everything together?
A study date?
Well played.
Safe and responsible.
No pressure,
but with potential
for things to move
to the next level.
Smooth.
Uh...
[laughs awkwardly]
Works for me.
When and where?
Anyone home?
[water running]
Eve?
I thought you were
at the funeral.
I was.
I'd say
you should've been there,
but it was pretty bleak.
Red Rush's girlfriend
had a meltdown, and...
[gasps]
You okay?
Hiccups.
Hmm.
Anything happening?
Is Rex around?
Rex?
Eve, hang on a sec...
[shower running]
[man moans]
You piece of shit!
[Rex] Babe, wait!
Hang on!
I knew there was a reason
you skipped the funeral!
-Just-just wait a second!
-Don't even...
Oh, god!
Are you kidding me, Kate?
I-I can't believe this.
Eve...
Oh, I am such an idiot.
Rex said you're dating
Invincible now.
Said that you guys
talked about it.
What?
Oh, don't give me that.
It's true.
What did you expect, huh?
It's not true,
and whatever I expected,
I guess I was wrong,
about both of you.
Hold on!
This?
This doesn't mean shit!
They're not even the real Kate!
We're all the real Kate.
Okay, I...
I didn't...
That's technically not what I...
But you know what I mean, right?
[Mark] Is that Demi-God?
Oh, Shrapnel!
[Robot] And Burly,
Pangea, Bug-Eye...
It's the crowning achievement
of any crusader's career
to be selected for
the New Guardians of the Globe,
which makes me wonder again
why you won't try out.
I know.
I talked it over
with my dad.
He wants to train me himself.
Plus, my mom would kill me
if I miss any more school.
Then why are you here?
Are you kidding?
Like I'd miss this?
Oh, my god,
there's Fight Force.
Why'd they even come here?
Despite your name,
I believe you underestimate
yourself, Invincible.
I'll still be around, helping.
When does this all get started?
["Rocket Fuel"
by De La Soul/DJ Shadow plays]
Thank you all
for coming here today.
♪ Ladies and gentlemen... ♪
The Guardians of the Globe
were more
than a group of heroes.
♪ Ladies and gentlemen... ♪
-They were icons.
-♪ Are you ready? ♪
Those of you
who pass our trials
will be among the elite...
♪ Get ready y'all ♪
[♪♪♪]
-♪ Get ready ♪
-[chuckling]
...The best of the best.
[♪♪♪]
[roaring]
♪ We giving a show ♪
♪ But can you rock it
like rocket fuel? ♪
♪ Space out your mind? ♪
♪ But can you rock it
like rocket fuel? ♪
Needless to say,
not all of you
will be up to the challenge.
Ouch.
What's up with her?
No idea.
Those of you who are
up to the challenge
will succeed
not just by the uniqueness
of your abilities,
but by the uniqueness
of your tactics...
your adaptability...
[bellowing]
...the agility of your minds.
[whistles]
♪ This be the green light, go
Tires burn the pavement ♪
♪ People wanna know
where Mase, Pos' and Dave went ♪
♪ Still here
Still in ya ear ♪
♪ With a style so hot ♪
♪ You'll see
where all the sun rays went ♪
♪ Legs, arms, and head
all being moved in a frenzy ♪
♪ The blends
we all the right cred' ♪
♪ Meaning credentials ♪
♪ Best of both worlds ♪
♪ When we rocking over pearls
in the instrumental ♪
♪ Are you ready? Ready!
Set? Set! ♪
♪ Jump to the rhythm
as hard as you can go ♪
♪ Keep it steady
Steady! ♪
♪ Let it rock ♪
♪ Turn it up
We giving a show ♪
♪ But can you rock it
like rocket fuel? ♪
♪ Space out your mind? ♪
Oh, yeah!
♪ But can you rock it
like rocket fuel? ♪
♪ Space out your mind? ♪
Rah!
[roaring]
[Robot] ...And perhaps
most importantly,
the strength of your character
and spirit.
That is what
truly makes a hero.
[applauding]
It is my pleasure to introduce
the new Guardians of the Globe.
Black Samson.
Shrinking Rae.
Dupli-Kate.
Monster Girl.
[laughing]
Aw, look at her,
she's adorable!
But isn't there, like,
an age requirement
for this ride?
Am I wrong?
'Cause this seems weird, right?
Rex...
I dunno, you're here.
Isn't there a dick size
requirement?
[Rex] I'm sorry?
For what, your tiny dick?
I mean, the way you've been
strutting around here,
you must be compensating
for something.
[laughter]
Somebody ought to teach you
some mother-fucking...
What the fuck?
[glass shatters]
[screaming]
Oof!
[groans]
[heavy thud]
Guess you missed my try-out.
[growling]
[deep, rumbling voice]
Still think I'm adorable?
[groans]
You little bitch.
Aw...
Now, that's adorable.
I'm gonna blast that smile
off your stupid, green face.
Please, stop,
this is hardly constructive.
Ha!
[roars]
Uh... is this okay?
He asked for it.
[Rex grunting]
Okay, enough.
Get lost, boy scout.
[Mark] I said, enough!
[grunts]
[woman] Invincible hit
that little girl!
Oh... shit.
Uh, look, I'm so sorry.
Nah, my bad.
The kid thing
sets me off every time,
and then it's like, "Rah!"
Beast mode.
Sorry about the dick joke.
I'm sure your junk
is awesome.
[groans] It's fine.
I'm good.
You're good.
You can... punch hard.
[groaning]
Didn't need your help, asshole.
Aw, Christ...
[Robot] As I was saying,
welcome to
the Guardians of the Globe,
Monster Girl...
I'm gonna shit blood.
...along with Rex Splode,
once he's recovered...
and our final member,
Atom Eve.
Thank you all for coming today.
We'll be making
a public announcement shortly.
[Eve] Robot.
No need to thank me.
I obviously needed
to remain impartial,
but I'm still delighted
so many members of the Teen Team
made the cut.
I can't be on the same team
as Rex and Kate.
What? Why?
Hey, wait!
Rex, what did you do?
[groans]
Thanks for the help, Robot.
Can't wait to be on your team.
Hey...
what's going on?
Rex cheated on me...
What?
...with Dupli-Kate,
all three of her.
Whoa.
Whoa...
I walked in on them.
Rex told her you and me
were a thing? Ugh.
Huh, what?
That's... crazy.
I didn't want to say it
while you were dating the guy,
but what an asshole.
He wasn't always,
but... yeah.
[sighs]
Well, that sucks.
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
As soon as the forensic
investigation has concluded,
we'll be moving into
the Guardians' headquarters.
Until then,
we'll be training here.
Breakfast is at 6:00 a.m.,
then close-in combat exercises
until lunch.
Where is Kate Prime?
Had a thing.
I can fill her in.
Okay, just to make it clear,
there is no universe
in which I wake up at 6:00 a.m.
and the world isn't on fire.
Come on, Robot.
We don't need
this boot camp bullshit.
It's us.
We're not on the Teen Team
any longer, Rex.
Exactly.
I'm sure you've had
a lot of experience
wrangling teenagers,
but I was with
the Guardians from day one.
Wow, thanks, Dad.
Maybe if you didn't
lose your powers,
you might've been there
to help the Guardians
on their last day.
I don't know you yet,
so I'm going to assume
that was a joke,
and I don't need
to beat your ass
until all you wanna do
is call me Dad again.
I don't know you either,
but we need a leader
we can look in the eye.
Not a bunch of ones and zeros.
No offense.
That's actually super offensive,
so wait, you think
you should be in charge?
I am the most experienced.
Yeah, at losing your powers.
Didn't I crack
that joke already?
Why are we even
putting up with this guy?
He wears a suit!
It takes batteries.
Let's just get Eve
back in here.
I'm new
to this whole team thing,
but I thought
it involved teamwork.
As did I.
Call me when
you figure it out.
I'll be in the gym.
Me too.
I'll go supervise.
[Dupli-Kate] No, you won't!
[Rex laughs] I can do
whatever I like.
Good first day, Robot.
I can't do
three combat exercises a day.
I'm on a rather tight timetable
to get this team operational.
Whenever I transform,
I get younger.
It's part of the curse
that gives me my powers.
I don't look it,
but I'm 24 years old.
I used to go by Monster Woman,
but it got too hard
to explain, so...
if you don't want to start
changing my diapers,
three exercises a day
are too much for me.
I didn't...
Of course, my apologies.
It must be difficult.
Try having a normal relationship
looking like this.
The guys who are interested
are either
going through puberty,
or popping up
on sex offender registries.
I understand what it's like
for the world to look at you
and see one thing,
never knowing the truth
of what's inside.
How can you understand?
You're a robot.
Pathetic.
[William] This has gotta go.
Hide this.
Toss this.
What? Stop.
Hey, being a geek
is cool now, okay?
So, maybe Amber
likes comics, too.
You thought of that?
Ya dick.
I'm not talking about
the comics,
I'm talking about
the dirty clothes,
the dishes,
the tissues.
Uh...
Better.
Okay, I brought you
some homework.
A little Naomi Klein.
A touch of Margaret Atwood.
Some Ta-Nehisi Coates.
I haven't read any of those.
[sighs] But she has,
so get started.
It'll show Amber
you're interested in her.
She's also into spicy foods,
stand-up comedy,
and fourth-wave feminism.
What?
I read her file.
I asked around at school.
It's just a study date,
not a first date.
Mark, every date
should feel like a first date.
[doorbell rings]
[Debbie] Mark!
Your friend is here!
[dishes clattering]
Go! Out the back way.
You can thank me later
when you call me,
and tell me exactly
how it all went.
[Amber] Hi, Mrs. Grayson.
I'm Amber.
Um, William said
I should read it
to show you
that I'm interested-
interesting-
and I will,
but this is more me.
An honest man.
I like that.
So...
you're into comics.
Is it that obvious?
[chuckles]
What's your favorite?
Oh, man, I can't pick
a favorite,
but...
Ooh, this one is about a guy
who's an underwater welder,
and starts seeing ghosts
on the bottom of the ocean,
and this one is about
a Jack Russell terrier
who's a master
of the metaphysical arts.
Seance Dog?
Cool.
You mind if I borrow it?
I mean, just to show you
that I'm interested.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
[Mark's cell phone rings]
Okay...
don't know who that is.
Um, I figured we should start
with global issues, and then...
[cell phone rings again]
Sorry.
Must be a robo-call.
Ha, this should do it.
So Ms. Walker says
we should focus on the...
[phone rings]
I'm gonna run
and use your bathroom
while you deal with that.
Yeah, uh, down the hall
on the left.
[beeping dismiss button]
Whoa!
[sighing]
Christ almighty.
I didn't think
she would ever leave.
Hey!
Oh, what are you...
How did you know Amber...
Are you spying on me?
You wanna be
a super hero, right?
Fame, glory, get the pretty gal?
I mean, that's sexist, but okay.
Well, then, the whole concept
of personal privacy
or me time? [scoffs]
That's out the window.
When the world needs you,
you answer your goddamn phone!
Don't worry,
she hasn't flushed yet.
I don't even work for you!
And you never will,
not unless you show
a little respect,
and decide if you want to be
a superhero or not.
Right now?
Yes, Mark, right now.
Okay, yes.
I want to help.
What's the problem?
Rogue supervillain.
Public in danger.
Eve's already en route.
Here, so we can talk on the go.
Eve's gonna be there?
Oh, did that just
sweeten the deal?
What? No.
I mean, um...
Where?
Where is this... at?
Mount Rushmore.
Okay.
What state is that again?
What do they teach you kids
in school these days?
Who were you talking to?
Oh, um...
Yeah, the thing with the, uh,
the phone, it's, um...
It was a friend of my dad's,
and, uh...
I forgot I'd promised
I'd help him
with this thing, um...
Now?
How's it going in here?
I brought snacks.
[Cecil in earpiece]
South Dakota.
[Eve] We know where
Mount Rushmore is, Cecil.
[Cecil] I wouldn't be
asking for your help,
but Omni-Man's dealing with
a kaiju ten time zones away,
and the new Guardians
are a shit show,
so here we are.
Target is Doc Seismic.
He has a Ph.D. in seismology,
so the doc thing,
that's legit.
Problem is, he made himself
a pair of earthquake gloves.
What's he want?
Even he doesn't seem to know.
Working theory
says brain damage
from a side effect
of those gloves.
He basically gets a concussion
every time he uses them.
So your basic
mad scientist deal.
Have fun, kids,
and try to remember,
that's a national treasure
down there.
[crowd screaming in panic]
[ground rumbling]
[evil laughter]
You've come to pray
at this obscene monument?
They were oppressors!
Racists!
Slave owners!
I give you a new god
worthy of worship!
Bow before Doc Seismic!
Rah!
Hah!
[ground rumbling]
[crumbling]
[panicked screams]
Run! This way!
Hurry! Hurry!
[laughs wickedly]
The great emancipator?
He'll emancipate you...
from your lives!
Wow, man,
I'm still working
on my one-liners,
but that one is really bad.
Ha ha!
That's how you get ahead
in life.
See, it's not quite there,
it's not there.
No argument from me.
Now die!
[grunts]
Ah, thanks.
Anytime.
We need to take out
his gloves.
[Mark] Those aren't gloves.
Gloves have fingers.
They're more, uh...
earthquake bracelets?
Ha! You're wearing
earthquake bracelets!
[grunts with effort] H'yah!
Y'ah!
[cackling wickedly]
You should be on my side!
We could tear down
the old power structure,
build a new order!
I mean, look at the costume
they've got you in.
Talk about pandering
to gender roles.
I designed my own costume,
and I thought your doctorate
was in seismology?
Undergrad in sociology
and women's studies.
I had a minor
in African Dance,
but enough politics!
H'wah!
-[gasps]
-Oh...
[grunts]
-Whoa!
-Oh!
[ground rumbling]
[gasps]
[child screams]
[screaming]
Mark!
Shit!
[screaming]
Bah!
[crackling]
[panting]
[grunts]
[yelps]
Oof! Oh...
[screams]
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Eve! Eve!
Eve!
[Eve] Invincible!
I got you.
He's slipping.
Ah, God dammit.
I should have spent more time
working on the jet pack!
[cackling]
H'ah!
Ugh!
[screams]
[gasps]
Look out!
[Eve chuckles]
Wow, that guy is toast.
Oh, I see,
so, like, none of these
sound good, huh?
Oh, crap, I gotta go!
I-I'll talk to you later, Eve!
Thanks!
You're welcome.
[panting]
Whoa, slow down.
What's up?
Cecil asked me to save
Mount Rushmore,
but I left Amber waiting
in the room so I gotta...
You left a girl in your room
while you flew off
to deal with a crisis?
Mm-hmm.
Good.
I mean, not good for her,
but good.
That's the tricky part
of the job,
balancing what you wanna do,
with what you need to do.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Remember, you're not just
a superhero, Mark.
You're a Viltrumite.
We have... responsibilities
that normal humans don't.
Right.
Yeah, thanks.
Hey, one last piece
of fatherly advice, okay?
You might wanna change.
Oh, crap.
Dad, you got a little...
here.
[grunting with effort]
I am so sorry.
I've been sitting here
for an hour.
I know.
Uh... Oh, that's a good one.
What'd you-
what'd you think?
Why did you even agree
to hang out
if you weren't gonna hang out?
I do want to hang out.
I just didn't think that...
Could've fooled me.
I don't even know why I came.
Okay, then, why did you come?
You didn't even know I existed
until I stood up to Todd.
For the record,
Todd kicked your ass.
that's absolutely true.
I've had guys throw punches
for me before,
but you're the first one
who stood there and took 'em.
Twice.
I wanted to know the kind of guy
that would do that.
An idiot?
[chuckles] Maybe.
Maybe not.
So, what now, hmm?
I finished
all the review questions
while you were off
saving the world or whatever.
It's big, sir.
Really big.
First time I've seen Omni-Man
on the ropes like that.
[low growling]
Also, it might not be dead.
[Cecil] Huh.
Put it on ice.
You never know
when something like that
might come in handy.
Yes, sir.
Oh, good God!
Calamari for dinner?
[chuckling]]
Get that off my counter!
Aw, you sure?
It's considered a delicacy
in some places,
and an aphrodisiac.
[scoffs]
Like you need it.
Did you call Cecil?
About putting
some protection on the house.
I was kinda busy.
Nolan...
Yeah, I'll take care of it.
Thank you.
Hey, don't forget
I just took down
a freakin' kaiju
and saved the world.
Your husband's a badass.
Yeah, well, you're not
the only badass in this family.
I sold a house today
that had a double homicide.
I told them lightning
never strikes twice.
[gasps]
Are you seriously
gonna put that on the grill?
["Let It All Go"
by Birdy and Rhodes plays]
♪ I've been sleepless at night ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't know
how I feel ♪
♪ I've been waiting on you ♪
♪ Just to say something real ♪
[explosions booming]
♪ There's a light on the road
and I think you know ♪
♪ Morning has come
and I have to go ♪
♪ But if we're strong enough
to let it in... ♪
Surprise!
[sighs] Look,
I screwed up, Eve.
I know I did, I just...
I just, I don't know
why I keep doing this.
I don't want to.
You know that, right?
You know I love you.
I know...
but that wasn't
an apology, Rex.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
Look, give me a do-over,
just this one time.
I'll be better.
I-I promise.
Good luck
with the new team, Rex.
♪ ...Strong enough
to let it go ♪
Fuck.
[♪♪♪]
[gasps]
Good for you, Mark.
[hissing]
[yawns]
Chow time.
You know the drill.
Ah, Thursday.
Chicken pot pie.
[guard] Everybody's favorite.
Stay back from the door.
[sniffs]
[sighs]
Stay back from the door.
Huh?
Shit.
Ah!
Ah, sorry, Pete.
[grunts]
[groans]
[lock buzzes open]
Hmm...
Damn.
Chicken pot pie night.
Mm...
[heavy knock on door]
How?
Obvious.
As the original article,
my intellect's undiluted
by the cloning process
that created you.
[dryly] Oh, please.
Just open the door.
Say it.
You cheap, genetically
inferior knock-off...
Say it,
or stay here forever.
[sighs]
I'm the clone.
[Mauler #2] Yes, you are.
This way.
["Chase Me" by Danger Mouse
and Run The Jewels plays]
[alarm wailing]
♪ Whoo! ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
♪ Gangster like you
wake up in Dickies ♪
♪ And load the clippy ♪
♪ The reign of our ascension ♪
♪ Make statisticians
feel sickly ♪
♪ Accountants
they get snippy ♪
♪ They never counted
so quickly ♪
♪ Got 'em up sniffin' yak up
off an abacus for a living ♪
♪ Crime authors ♪
♪ Autobiographically bastards ♪
♪ Pain passin'
put a pain in your brain ♪
♪ Style droppin' the drums
and stun all goggles ♪
♪ Small talkers
get launched on... ♪
Clear a path.
[grunting with effort]
♪ Tick tock ♪
♪ You got until
the hands on the clock stop ♪
♪ I'm baggin' a bag
then I'm backing out ♪
♪ Better back off ♪
♪ That's why
I'm outta here, baby ♪
♪ Before these clowns put me
down in the ground, baby ♪
♪ I'm running reds 'til
I'm out of this town, baby ♪
♪ You want your money back?
Chase me ♪
[alarm blaring]
We have a benefactor, it seems.
[hatch thuds]
[grunting]
[mechanism humming nearby]
Huh?
Multi-phased fusion generator
in the 30-megawatt range.
[hydraulics whirring]
What now?
I'm surprised
you don't see it,
you being the original
and all.
[grunts]
[gasping]
[power ramping up]
[roaring]
[blasts squelching]
[bellowing roar]
[raspy breaths]
I'd say
I'll miss you, brother...
but I can always
make another one.
[drone buzzing softly]
[door opens]
So, give me an update.
You get my team ready
for the deep end yet?
We still have work to do,
but I feel confident
in the progress
we've made today.
[dog barking]
[keyboard clacking softly]
[exhales]
[frost crackling]
[gasps]
My apologies.
Didn't mean to scare.
What are you doing in my house?
Seeking... information.
Clues.
Answers.
Answers to what?
That night, the massacre.
Still not clear to me.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You need to leave now.
Seven dead.
One alive.
Your husband.
Was hoping you could
make that piece fit.
Well, you'll have to ask him.
Did.
Answers were...
unsatisfactory.
Why do you care?
Escaped from hell.
Seek justice for others
to save own soul.
Husband told you nothing?
Not a whisper
to soothe your fears?
No.
He didn't say anything.
[grumbles] Hmm...
You have a lovely home.
[Nolan] Debbie?
You all right?
I thought I heard something.
I'm fine.
I was just coming to bed.
[♪♪♪]