[Nolan]
Hey, I need my costume back.
It's classified,
and I want it back.
Am I important to you, Mark?
I'm gonna do better.
Maybe if you didn't
lose your powers,
you might have been there
to help the Guardians
on their last day.
I'm not even sure
I want to do this anymore!
Welcome to the world
of the living, Clone.
I need your expertise
in tissue growth.
I'm here for you.
Whatever you need.
You want to talk,
I'll listen.
[Machine Head] Murder.
These.
Assholes!
No! No, no, no!
[Amber] I thought
Mark would be here tonight.
I really did.
[teens giggling]
[laughing together]
[branches rustling]
[screams]
[burps]
Oh, hey, excuse me.
'Sup, ladies?
What the hell?
You scared us,
you creep.
Why were you hiding
in the bushes?
Oh, my god!
I wasn't hiding
in the bushes.
I was drinking
But that's not important.
What's important-- [burps]
--is that I'm motherfuckin'
Doug Cheston!
[gulping]
[belches]
Who?
My dad owns--
[body slumps]
My dad owns
Cheston Pharmaceutical,
and like, half this univer--
--and like,
half this university.
Didn't your dad
hike up prices
on that baby medicine
everyone needs?
Totally, yeah!
Anyway, I'm gonna inherit
all that shit soon,
'cause my dad's mad old.
So...
Do one, or, ideally, all of you,
want to have sex tonight,
and get in on the ground floor
of my inheritance?
-Gross.
-Ew! No way.
[scoffs] You don't know
what you're missing.
[laughs, scoffing]
Yeah, we so do!
It's me!
I'm what you're missing!
Me and my huge--
[grunts]
--trust fund.
[groans]
What the...?
Hey, where am I?
[DA Sinclair] Oh, hello.
[chuckles] I know,
you're confused,
but I'm sure
you're used to that.
Just stay quiet and still,
and soon you'll be feeling
better than ever.
What?
What's going on?
You're going through
a metamorphosis,
a miracle
that will take you
from useless boil
on the behind
of this crooked world,
to a brave explorer
charting a shining future
for all humanity--
Nerd!
[guffaws]
Who talks like that?
You do!
You're a nerd, nerd!
[grunts, straining]
[gasps]
[straining] Hey!
Let me up, asshole!
If this is some joke,
or some weird sex shit,
my dad's gonna sue you
into the Stone Age!
Oh, Jesus!
Oh! Oh, shit!
[grunting]
[screams]
What the fuck is that?
[DA Sinclair]
No histrionics, please.
What the fuck did you do?
Or I'll be forced to--
-Oh, my god!
-[blade slices]
[squelching]
[gurgling]
I think we can all agree
you're better
without vocal cords--
[clang]
--and don't worry
about those prototypes.
You're going to be different.
You're going to be beautiful.
You're going to be--
[paramedic] Make a hole!
Keep moving! Careful!
Prep O.R. 3, 6, and 8!
-Pre-op!
-Clamp that vein!
Keep an eye on that for me.
I've got
multiple skull fractures
and cranial swelling.
She's convulsing!
Keep her airway clear.
These numbers
don't make any sense.
Watch out!
Hot transit
needs care immediately.
One, two, three.
She's drowning
in her own blood.
Get her intubated, now!
Toss me the saline.
Blood pressure's cratering.
Someone get Dr. Barclay in here.
I'm getting a line started.
Find out what kind of blood
she can take.
The needle won't go in.
Shit!
Uh...
I've studied Monster Girl's
physiology extensively.
Please stand aside.
What?
Get him out of here!
Security!
[guns cocking]
You can attempt to remove me,
you may even succeed,
but then she dies,
or you can assist me,
and we can save her life.
Choose now.
Shh... I'm here now.
Monster Girl's only hope
is if we can activate
her innate healing abilities.
Begin a saline infusion
of 2% belladonna root,
5% wolfsbane.
We don't have that.
Then get it.
Nano-sutures.
He's fibrillating!
[monitor flatlining]
[charging]
Clear!
[shock thumps]
[monitor flatlining]
Again!
[charging]
[shock thumps]
[flatline drones]
Going to max charge!
[charging]
[shock thumps]
One more time.
[flatline beeps]
Dammit.
Huh?
[energy surging]
-What the hell?
-[glass shattering]
[circuits crackling]
[energy surges and falls silent]
What just happened?
[man] I have no idea.
[heartbeat beeping steadily]
This is bad.
He's got a hole
all the way through him.
[woman] Careful.
-Pulse is dropping, people!
-I'm on it!
[woman]
Spinal damage seems likely.
[man] Thank God,
whatever tore him up was sharp.
[female voice, distant] Mark...
Mark...
Mark?
Mom?
[gasps] Oh...
sweetheart.
I knew you'd pull through.
[groans]
How long was I out?
Six days.
Six days?
No...
No, no, I was supposed to, um...
Amber--
It's okay,
I covered for you.
Told her you got hit by a bus,
which, from the looks of you,
isn't far off.
Black Samson?
Monster Girl?
Still unconscious.
It's not your fault.
Darkblood crack yet?
You know him.
He barely talks
when he wants to.
Let me take a swing.
I'll make him talk.
As fascinating
as it would be
to watch an unstoppable force
meet an immovable object,
I prefer to keep
these kind of things in-house.
Did he do it?
Did he murder
the Guardians?
We don't know.
What's more interesting to me
is why he would do it.
He's a demon.
There's your why.
I thought I knew him,
that's all.
Mark never told you
he was taking on
Machine Head
all by his lonesome?
Yeah, he told me.
Told me he wasn't
gonna take the bait.
[chuckles]
What's so funny
about that?
You're the most powerful man
on the planet,
but even your kid
won't listen to you.
What, this doesn't
happen on Viltrum?
No.
It doesn't.
[chuckles] Hmm.
Mark's a human teenager, Nolan.
It's what they do.
It's reassuring, really.
[Amber] You do look like
you got run over.
Yeah, that's me.
The guy who doesn't know
how traffic lights work.
I still can't believe
you wouldn't let me
see you in the hospital.
They had weird rules
about visitors.
Eve only knew I was there
because, um, she heard
from William.
What?
I'd basically already
dumped you that night.
I know...
and I've thought a lot
about that
these last couple of days.
Remember
when I first called you?
After you made Todd
give me your number?
Yeah.
I was terrified,
and I could barely
talk straight,
and I messed it all up,
but you let me
start over.
And?
Can we do that again?
Start over?
You're right.
Yeah, I don't deserve...
to start over.
Hey, handsome Mark Grayson.
I'm glad you've still got
that pretty face of yours.
[chuckles]
Me too.
So, uh...
wanna hang out sometime?
Sure.
[♪♪♪]
[William] Both ways, Mark.
You need to look both ways
before you cross the street.
Did you skip kindergarten
the day they taught that?
[chuckles]
Guess so.
Hey, we haven't hung out
for a while. We should--
Because someone's
the king of excuses.
"I've got to study."
"I need to help my dad
with work."
"I'm infectious."
Blah, blah, blah.
Okay.
Well, there's no school
on Friday.
Let's catch a movie
or something.
Love to.
Can't.
Remember Rick?
The guy you couldn't stop
talking about last summer?
You make it sound like
I was obsessed or something.
Anyway, he's at Upstate U.
I'm going for a tour on Friday.
Staying over.
They have
a very handsome
pre-med program.
Did I say handsome?
I meant "world-class,"
but also, handsome.
Can I come?
What?
I want to come.
Okay...
And I want to bring Amber.
Hold on--
Please, William.
I need this.
[soft knock]
Eve!
Come in.
Mark, I wanted--
I never got to thank you
for talking to Amber
when I was hurt,
so... [sighs]
Thanks.
Going somewhere?
Oh, this guy
William's crushing on
goes to Upstate U.
William's going
for a tour,
and I convinced him
to let me and Amber
tag along.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
I'm sorry.
Um, if you want to come,
that's totally cool.
I'm just trying to start over
with Amber, you know?
Show her I'm serious this time.
That's okay.
I'm skipping college anyway.
What? Why?
Your grades
are way better than mine.
When I was at
the community center with Amber,
something clicked for me.
I think I can help more people
by just... helping them,
you know?
I don't have to wait
for some alien invasion
or the Lizard League's
next attack.
I can irrigate deserts,
stop natural disasters,
bring food to the starving.
You know,
make a real difference.
Yeah. I get it.
Huh.
I thought you'd try
and talk me out of it.
Rex would have.
I really messed up downtown.
Black Samson and Monster Girl
almost died
because of me.
So I get it.
Maybe fighting off
alien invasions
isn't in either of our futures.
Maybe we both need
a fresh start.
[Debbie calls] Mark!
William and Amber
are here.
Okay, Mom!
-[soft whoosh]
-So where are you--
You okay?
Yeah. Fine.
Just sore.
[bangs roof]
Come on, slowpoke!
Let's hit the road!
Okay, be careful.
Don't have too much fun.
No drinking.
No drugs.
And no sex!
[William laughs, Mark groans]
No sex. Got it.
I'll take good care
of them, Mrs. Grayson!
[♪♪♪]
[revs engine, tires squealing]
[horn honks, teens laugh]
Tell me more
about this Rick guy.
Oh, man.
I can't wait
for you to meet him.
He's like,
first of all, tall.
Amazing hair.
Thick as a horse's mane.
That's good?
-Yes.
Rick's style?
Incredible.
A perfect combo
of street and prep.
Did I mention his teeth?
Little white bricks of joy--
Going out?
Need to pick up
some dry cleaning,
something for dinner.
I won't be long.
I'll come along--
You're on a deadline
for the book.
Isn't that what you told me?
Or was I mistaken?
No, that's right.
Then you've got work to do,
don't you?
[car engine starting]
[William] I mean,
can a person
even have an eight-pack?
Anyhoo,
I don't wanna bore you guys
any more about Rick.
-Ooh, except that he's--
-We get it!
You're in love with the guy.
What? No.
I mean, Rick's amazing,
but love him?
No.
Oh, my god,
here he comes!
William!
Come here!
What's up, Rick?
These are my friends,
Mark and Amber.
We've heard
so much about you.
Hey.
Nice to meet you guys.
Let me grab your bags.
I got my dorm room
all set up for us.
[♪♪♪]
It's gonna be
a great weekend.
I just don't understand
why can't you do your new
superhero helping job
from here?
You know why.
[Dad, shouting angrily]
Samantha...
Samantha!
-[banging on wall]
-Samantha!
The back door
is still there.
I need a fresh start.
Somewhere new.
Somewhere that's not here.
What about school?
Or-or college?
I've got enough credits
to graduate,
and college can wait--
Samantha!
I'm not going to watch you
ruin your life
on some hippie-dippie
find-yourself bullshit--
Adam!
I mean it.
This is the opposite
of what you should be doing
with your life.
And what would that be, Dad?
You want a fresh start?
Give up this superhero crap.
You can't save the world,
Samantha.
It's gonna get you killed.
The worst day of my life
was when you got powers.
Wow, that hurts much more
than I thought it would.
I just want
what's best for you.
A normal life.
A house.
A husband.
Kids...
That's what's best for you, Dad.
Not for me.
Samantha!
You get your feet
back on the ground now!
Bye, Mom.
Bye, Dad.
Samantha!
This place
is pretty cool.
It's also one of the best
med schools in the country.
That's why I arranged
a little biology class sit-in
for you guys.
You're still thinking pre-med,
right, William?
Yup.
[whispering]
He remembered!
[chuckles]
[professor] It may look
the same from the outside,
but the chance of heart failure
doubles
with each decade of life.
What can we do about that?
Eat better, sure.
Exercise helps.
Drugs, hmm.
But fundamentally
our parts wear out.
Our focus is therefore
on extending
quality of life,
even if we can't extend
life itself--
[DA Sinclair] Oh, please.
Ah, Mr. Sinclair.
Once again, it seems
you have an opinion to share?
I have the truth to share.
Who's the dick?
[Rick] DA Sinclair.
He's here on a genius grant,
and makes sure
everyone knows it.
When you want to travel quickly,
you don't run,
you get in a car.
When you need to fly
to another country,
you don't flap your arms,
you get on a plane.
We're all aware
how travel works, Mr. Sinclair.
Your point?
All human failings
are simply
engineering challenges
crying out to be solved.
We're machines,
and the sooner
we recognize that,
the sooner we'll reach
our true potential.
Dramatic much?
I'm sorry?
I'm not.
You're being a jerk.
What's your problem, Sinclair?
My problem?
My problem is
this school of idiots.
[clears throat]
MIT courted me.
Yale offered me a lab--
You should take it.
[muffled giggles]
[exhales]
You're impressive, Rick.
Muscular.
Assertive.
Classic alpha male.
Hey!
Don't say those...
compliments to him.
Mr. Sinclair...
you can return
when you're ready to learn.
Then I'll see you
at exams.
Rick.
[students murmuring]
As I was saying,
quality of life,
not quantity.
["Knock Me Off My Feet"
by SOAK plays]
[♪♪♪]
♪ I've always done
the best I could ♪
♪ To get out of
my neighborhood... ♪
Well, I like the view.
♪ Growing up I spilt my blood ♪
♪ But you're still my home ♪
♪ Saturday night
on the highest wall ♪
♪ It doesn't exist-- ♪
It's a start.
♪ --the law ♪
♪ You can, you can
knock me off my feet... ♪
Was it just me,
or was that DA guy
checking you out?
[laughs]
I bet you have
that problem a lot.
Oh, please.
I feel sorry for him.
He needs friends
more than anything.
[William] That is
so evolved of you.
You okay?
You don't still have
a concussion or something
you haven't told me
about, do you?
What? Uh, no.
I'm good,
I'm really good.
If you two want
some time to wander,
we can meet back here
in a few hours.
That's a great idea.
See you both back here
in a while!
It's okay if you're late.
Come on,
let's go see what this place
is really like.
♪ You can, you can
knock me off my feet ♪
♪ But I won't stop now
you can take a seat ♪
♪ You can, you can
knock me off my feet ♪
♪ But I won't stop now
you can take a seat ♪
♪ You can, you can
knock me off my feet ♪
♪ But I won't stop now
you can take a seat ♪
♪ You can, you can
knock me off my feet ♪
♪ But I won't back down
you can take a seat ♪
♪ You can, you can
knock me off my feet ♪
♪ But I won't stop now
no, I won't be beat ♪
♪ You can, you can
knock me off my feet... ♪
You're all smiles now.
[chuckles]
Yeah.
I guess I kinda like it here.
It's okay.
A bit too fancy, maybe,
but I hear they do have
a good social-justice program.
[Mark] What do you think
about coming here?
Together, I mean.
If you want that
to happen,
you need to get
your grades up,
Mark Grayson.
You're aware
you need to apply
to college, right?
I'm serious.
I think
this is what I want.
You know, when you start
a sentence with "I think,"
you automatically murder
90% of any romance in it--
This is what I want.
You and me, here.
Together.
Okay.
Really?
Sure. Why not?
[William laughs]
Hey, lovebirds!
Did you have a good time--
[explosion rumbling]
[students scream in panic]
[screams of terror]
What the hell is that?
Holy shit.
[emits a gurgling screech]
[growling]
[panicked screams]
[emits hoarse shriek]
Oh, my god, get back!
Everybody, get back!
[screaming]
Hurry!
[monster growling]
Guys! Help me!
[panicked screaming]
[snarling]
[screams]
[crashing]
[snarling]
[grunts]
[Amber] Mark!
Come on!
[groans in pain]
William!
[yelps]
[wheezing and spluttering]
Get away from him,
you bastard!
[William choking]
No!
[choking and grunting]
Mark!
Mark?
[metal clangs]
[gasps] Huh?
[groaning and straining]
[groaning]
[coughs]
-Mark?
-Run!
[grunting]
[body slamming heavily]
[grunts]
[grunts, smashing]
[burbling]
[grunts]
[blows thud]
[groans]
[snarling]
[roaring]
Oof!
[snarling]
[panting]
[bones crunch]
[snarling]
No! Mark!
[groaning]
[gasps]
[yelps]
[breathing hard]
[snarling]
[grunts] Huh?
[gasps]
[metal parts crunching]
[groaning in confusion]
[wheezing scream]
[squelching and dripping]
What the hell?
[William]
Holy shit. Holy shit.
You're Invincible.
-You. Are. Invincible--
-Shh. Please!
You can't tell anyone.
I can't believe this.
It all makes sense now.
Holy shit!
Holy shit.
[Amber] William!
Are you okay?
No.
I'm definitely not okay.
I mean, I am okay.
I'm just-- wow.
Who was that?
That...
That was M... vincible.
William.
You saved my life.
What? Me?
I mean... yes.
Of course, I did.
You're welcome.
[Mark] Guys!
The police are on their way--
Where the hell did you go?
Um, I ran for help?
I tried to get security,
but there wasn't anyone--
You lying piece of shit--
Wait, no!
This isn't
what it looks like--
You took off.
You left us here
with that thing.
Amber, no. I...
That's not what happened.
You said
you wanted to start over.
You said that.
You promised.
Even Eve vouched for you,
and then you do this?
Eve was wrong about you.
So was I.
Wait!
Amber!
[DA Sinclair]
I turn my back for one second,
and the ungrateful half-wit
slips away?
That's it.
That's the last time
I leave anyone's
frontal lobe intact.
Hmm...
Classic alpha male.
[police sirens wailing]
Make the world
you want to live in.
[monitors beeping steadily]
I don't like
those interferon counts.
We need to do something
about that.
My god.
[metal creaking and straining]
[circuits shorting]
Those are normal levels
for Monster Girl.
She has a curse,
not a disease.
When she was injured,
I immediately dispatched
a drone to the Arctic.
This is a Cerulean Cosmos.
It contains
a unique molecule
that I believe will add 60%
to her chances of survival.
It was well guarded.
Use biomass sonification
to extract
the primary compounds,
then call me for isolation
and purification.
[Samson]
You really care for her.
Samson... good
to see you awake.
and yes, I do.
You're a machine.
How does a machine
have emotions?
I'm programmed to care
for all humans.
I beg to differ.
You didn't get your ass whooped
in the Arctic for me.
[groans, straining]
So I take it, we won?
[old time ballad plays]
♪ ...Hasty words
that seem to--♪
[turns music volume down]
[Art] Thanks...
Thanks for coming.
Can I get you a drink
or something?
You want to sit first?
Catch up?
Thanks, Art, but...
I know,
I know.
I'm just trying to put it off.
I spent the last few days
going over it
top to bottom,
like you asked.
Show me.
You sure, Deb?
[sighs heavily]
[tablet beeps]
See these flecks?
They look like gold,
but they're much harder.
I've only seen them
one other place--
War Woman's armor.
[beeps tablet]
Sodium Crystals.
Aquarus.
[Art] Those are from Darkwing's
throwing weapons.
He's tangled with
a few of my other clients.
[tablet beeps]
Are those burns?
Friction burns.
From something moving real fast.
Red Rush.
[gasps]
Okay.
Okay, this--
this only proves Nolan
and the Guardians fought.
Maybe they attacked him first?
Maybe-- maybe he was trying
to protect their legacy?
Maybe...
but there's also this.
Blood begins to oxidize
when exposed to air.
I can measure it.
See how long
since it was spilled.
This is the oldest blood
on the suit.
Nolan struck first.
Don't tell anyone.
Not Cecil.
No one.
Debbie...
I'm too scared to tell anyone.
Amber, I was trying to help!
Oof!
There's no way
I'm sharing a room
with you tonight.
Uh, well,
that's my bedroom,
but okay.
That's cool.
Mark, you can bunk
out here with us.
Oh, yeah, totally.
Sorry about this.
Oh, don't sweat it.
I'll go down to the store
and grab some beer.
Maybe by then,
things will cool down,
and we can get this weekend
back on track.
Sound good?
I'll stay here.
Make sure they don't
murder each other.
[door closes]
[panicky]
Are... you...
kidding me?
Shh!
I feel gross.
I'm taking a shower.
[door closes]
You're Invincible!
Not now, man!
Sorry, sorry,
but holy shit,
you're Invincible!
[sighs]
And you never told me?
["Get Gone"
by Deap Valley plays]
[♪♪♪]
♪ Come on, let's go! ♪
♪ I think I wanna get gone ♪
♪ Where are we going? ♪
♪ Where have we gone ♪
♪ I wanna roll to the motion
of the ocean in the sub ♪
♪ And ride, ride, ride, ride
baby, we gone ♪
♪ Where are we goin'?
Where are we goin'? ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
Your progress is...
satisfactory.
[Mauler] Satisfactory?
You know how hard it is
to grow cells
this quickly?
Yes.
That's why I hired you.
Exactly.
Now...
what's it for?
And whose DNA
did you steal?
Your work doesn't require
answers to those questions.
Maybe, maybe not,
but our work
does require payment.
When it's complete.
Then we might just leak
liquid ammonia
into the growth chamber.
New cells don't like
liquid ammonia.
Old cells don't like it either.
[chuckling]
You will receive
the schematics
when you finish your work,
and not a moment sooner.
Yeah, whatever.
Fine.
We'll call you.
[door closes]
Trust him?
[scoffs]
Then we need some insurance.
Grab a shovel.
[William] How long
have you been a superhero?
[Mark, wearily] William...
Three months?
Six months?
-Longer?
-Stop--
I'm your best friend.
Best friends
don't not tell best friends
they're superheroes!
[gasping]
Take me flying.
No.
I don't even wanna be
Invincible anymore.
Shut. Your. Mouth.
You being a superhero
is the coolest thing
that's ever happened to me.
Amber will forgive you.
She always does.
I'm not so sure this time.
Yeah, you might be right.
Now take me flying,
or I'm gonna tell everyone
you're Invincible.
Sorry not sorry.
[William yelps] Whoa-ho!
[distantly] Whoo! Yes!
There! Okay?
Can I try it on?
What?
Your suit! Can I--
Absolutely not!
[sighing]
[gasps]
Sorry!
Didn't mean to scare you.
It's fine.
Anyway.
I'm Kyle.
Good for you.
I'm sorry.
I'm Amber.
Low-key mega-party
at our house tonight.
A fraternity?
Yeah, but, like, the okay kind
that isn't super douche-y?
Yo, you guys hungry?
Should I grab some pizza
or something?
Love it.
No mushrooms, please.
Everything okay
with the lovebirds?
[Rick chuckles]
Yikes.
Well, I'll be back soon,
and we can deal with that--
[static]
Rick?
You there?
Hello?
Mark! Amber!
[Amber] She just left.
Got invited to some party.
Oh, shit, should I have
gone after her?
Get up!
Something happened
to Rick.
We were on the phone,
and it cut off.
We need to look for him.
I need to go after Amber.
What?
Just call him back.
He's not answering!
You don't want my help.
Every time
I try to be a hero,
I make things worse.
What if it's that thing
from earlier?
You saw me kill it.
It killed itself.
Whatever. It's dead.
Look, call me if you really
can't find Rick,
but I gotta
go after Amber first.
Sorry.
-[monitors beep steadily]
-That's the weird thing.
I feel better than ever.
Almost like before
I lost my powers.
Maybe I should get
my ass kicked more often.
Then rejoin the team
at Guardians HQ.
I will remain here
until Monster Girl recovers.
Yeah, all right.
See you later.
[yelps, startled]
I'm sorry,
I didn't mean to--
No, it's okay.
You just scared me.
[groans]
My head...
Did we win?
Black Samson asked
the same question.
Yes, we won.
In great part
due to your sacrifice.
[sighs] Thank god.
How's everyone else?
Or was I the only loser
who got the shit
kicked out of them?
Everyone else is fine.
Concerned about you,
but fine.
I'm happy you're awake.
Your recovery was...
tenuous at times.
You stayed with me?
I never left.
Hmm?
♪ Tell me where you are
and your location ♪
♪ We got drinks
and we kill 'em by the cases ♪
[exhales]
♪ I don't remember names
only remember faces... ♪
[gasps]
Rick? Rick!
[♪♪♪]
Hey!
Amber, right?
You showed!
[grunts with effort]
[groans in disgust]
Rick?
[splashing]
Are you there?
Rick?
[♪♪♪]
[Nolan laughs] And you...
you dressed him in plaid!
[laughing]
You know,
he had to wear that suit
when he met the President.
Well, let that be
a lesson to you,
never piss off your tailor.
[Nolan laughs]
What's the matter, Art?
You seem a little nervous.
No, no, just, uh, tired.
Lots of repairs this week.
I bet.
It's funny how quickly things
can fall apart.
One day,
it seems like you have
all the time in the world,
and then the next...
it's gone.
Oh?
Ah, don't listen to me.
I just wanted to swing by
and make sure our partnership
is still going strong.
Like you said,
never piss off
your tailor, right?
[music thumping, conversations]
[♪♪♪]
It's not all parties.
There's a ton
of great programs here.
The profs are solid,
the labs are new--
What?
You're a little nerdy
for a frat guy.
[laughs]
My girlfriend says
the same thing.
She's transferring here
next semester.
I miss her a ton.
You seeing anyone?
[sighs]
I was.
[♪♪♪]
[cell phone rings]
Not now, William.
[muffled screams]
[groaning] Mark!
I can't hear you.
I'll see you back
at Rick's dorm--
[signal crackling]
[gasps]
[♪♪♪]
[banging and pounding]
No!
[screaming in protest]
What did you do with Rick?
[grunts]
Why, the same thing
I'm about to do with you.
[tool whirring]
Shit, shit, shit...
William!
[splashing]
[gags]
William?
What did you do with William?
Whoa!
[punching and struggling]
[groans]
[wall crumbles]
-Whoa, William!
-A rematch.
Excellent.
I'm afraid I witnessed
that first scrap
and made a few
small improvements.
[groans]
Mark! Invincible!
He's turning people
into those things!
You make me sound
like a monster.
I'm not turning people
into anything.
I'm fixing
humanity's weaknesses.
[grunts]
[snarling]
[groaning]
[snarls]
[stomps, crushing rock]
[roars]
Oh, my god! Rick?
[groaning]
Stop! Don't do this!
It's no use
appealing to his emotions.
I removed them myself.
No!
[screams in grief]
[groans]
[slamming]
-[ribs cracking]
-[screams]
Rick? It's us! It's me!
[Mark groans]
We met last year!
At the lake!
Remember last summer?
The boathouse!
It changed my life, Rick.
I know it changed yours, too.
[blood splashing]
We had sex by the water!
It was the best thing
that ever happened to me!
Oh, that's a tad personal...
-[bone saw whirrs]
-No!
[screaming]
[Rick groans] William?
Yes, Rick! It's me!
Help us!
[punches squelching]
[gasps and moans]
Are you crying?
No... No!
Stop! You'll ruin yourself!
[circuit shorts]
[roars]
[shouting in rage]
[squelching]
[circuits shorting]
You brutes have set
humanity back decades!
[unsnapping shackles]
You're not
going anywhere, asshole!
[grunting]
[roaring]
[blood splashing]
Don't you understand?
This is about progress!
Science!
Saving the human race
from disease!
[gasping]
[grunts]
[slumps wetly]
[moans, mumbling]
[paramedic]
Want to check his pressure?
I'm sorry.
[winces]
I just lost it.
Don't beat yourself up.
I would've done the same thing.
What are you going
to do with him?
I figure the classic
lock him up
and throw away the key.
Impressive technology, though,
especially for something
built in a sewer.
Sick, you mean.
Hard to believe
they gave you a run
for your money like that.
[paramedic]
This guy's in bad shape.
Let's get him out.
Can you help them?
We'll do our best.
Go home, kid.
I'll take it from here.
♪ Late night thinkin' bout
many mistakes ♪
♪ I never meant to hurt you... ♪
[William sobbing]
♪ Late-night problems come
and I can't escape ♪
♪ I never meant to change you ♪
♪ I wish
that I could fix this... ♪
♪ I wish that it was easy... ♪
[♪♪♪]
[sighs]
♪ But I fucked up ♪
[front door opens and closes]
[distraught] Why?
Why what?
Josef.
Darkwing.
War Woman.
The others...
Why did you do it?
I didn't do anything--
[grunts]
Don't lie to me!
I know!
I know you killed them, Nolan!
You're drunk.
We'll talk about this tomorrow.
[grunts]
[breathing hard]
Fuck you, Nolan.
[door slams shut]
[glass shatters]
[fist slams]
[frogs and crickets chirping]
[shovel rasping]
I dunno, man.
My stepdad could lose
his job at the White House
for this.
Stop being a wuss, Matt.
This is gonna be epic,
and when it's all over,
we'll be the ones
calling the shots.
You sure it's gonna work?
You got the schnapps?
We dig up the Immortal,
drink from his skull,
and wham,
we get his powers.
Easy as shit, man.
It's just a rumor.
Dude, I saw it on Reddit.
[gasps]
[Mauler] Don't believe
everything you read
on the Internet... kids.