[♪♪]
[GEORGE]  SOME PEOPLE
YOU JUST NEVER FORGET.
IT'S LIKE THEY GET
BURNED INTO YOUR BRAIN.
OTHER PEOPLE
MAKE NO IMPRESSION AT ALL.
IT'S LIKE THEY'RE THERE...
AND THEN THEY'RE NOT.
CALL IT.
THAT ONE, SLEEPING.
THAT'S NOT A PERSON
UNDER THERE.
IS TOO, CURLED UP.
WHERE ARE THE LEGS?
MAYBE HE DOESN'T
HAVE ANY.
ROXY.WHAT?
NOT EVERYBODY MAKES IT
THROUGH LIFE INTACT.
WE ALL DIDN'T GET
A COZY,
COMFORTABLE LIFE
IN THE SUBURBS,
LITTLE GIRL.
COZY, MAYBE.
COMFORTABLE, NEVER.
CLOCK IS TICKING.
MAKE YOUR PICK.
HE LOOKS
LIKE A SIMMS.
GO ASK HIM--
MAYBE HE'LL GIVE YOU
A BITE OF HIS
SQUIRREL KEBAB.
UM... HI, EVERYONE.
GOOD MORNING.
[GEORGE CHUCKLES
AWKWARDLY]
I'M LOOKING FOR
A MISTER OR MISS A. SIMMS.
A. SIMMS?
WHO IS A. SIMMS?
BUELLER? ANYONE?
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
MAY I HAVE
YOUR ATTENTION, PLEASE?
WE DIDN'T
DO ANYTHING.
YOU CAN'T CITE US.
RELAX. I'M ON
A MISSION OF MERCY.
A. SIMMS.
WE HAVE A MISSING
PERSONS REPORT THAT
NEEDS TO BE CONFIRMED.
YOUR HAVE RICH...
AND LOVING RELATIVES
THAT THINK
YOU'RE DEAD.
WHAT THE FUCK?
SHIT.
[OBJECT WHISTLING]
[THUD]
EW.
I'VE ALWAYS SAID
LITTERING SHOULD BE
A CAPITAL OFFENSE.
PEOPLE. PEOPLE, BACK UP.
THIS IS A CRIME SCENE.
MONTANA?
IS IT MONTANA?
WHO'S MONTANA?
I'M MONTANA.
SHIT! ROXY, WHAT
JUST HAPPENED?
I GOT THE WRONG GUY!
NO I.D.
WHERE THE HELL IS
A. SIMMS?
I WAS ARTHUR SIMMS.
WHAT?
BUT I HAVEN'T
USED THAT NAME
SINCE I WAS 19.
WELL, HE'S JOHN DOE NOW.
REALLY?YEAH.
WE GET THESE GUYS
EVERY DAY.
NO I.D., NOBODY TO
CLAIM THEIR BODIES.
WHAT HAPPENS TO THEM?
UNMARKED GRAVES,
COURTESY OF THE COUNTY.
HARSH.
GEORGE, EVERYBODY
CAN'T GET A MONUMENT,
OR ELSE THE WORLD'D BE
ONE BIG-ASS GRAVEYARD.
YOU HUNGRY?
GIVE ME YOUR PEN.
GEORGE...
GEORGE. THIS IS NOT
YOUR PROBLEM.
NOT ANYMORE.
JOHN DOE, MY ASS.
FEEL GOOD
ABOUT YOURSELF NOW?
I DO.
HEY!
HEY, PUT THAT BACK!
HELLO! OFFICER?
HE'S STEALING.
TELL HIM TO PUT IT BACK.
NO, DON'T.
IT GETS COLD OUT HERE.
HE NEEDS IT.
HE NEEDS IT
MORE THAN I DO.
GOOD FOR YOU,
ARTHUR SIMMS.
CIRCLE OF LIFE, BABY.
[TEACHER]
BIG SMILES, EVERYONE.
LET'S SEE
THAT LINCOLN SPIRIT.
MR. HAMMOND...
ON MY SIGNAL.
STEVEN PEALE,
QUIT HORSING AROUND.
FACE FORWARD, PLEASE.
THANK YOU.
REGGIE LASS,
I KNOW YOU HAVE A SMILE
IN THERE SOMEWHERE!
WELL, CLASS, I GUESS
WE'LL ALL JUST HAVE TO
KEEP STANDING HERE
UNTIL MISS LASS DECIDES
TO GET WITH THE PROGRAM.
LASS! TELL HER YOU DON'T
NEGOTIATE WITH TERRORISTS.
SANDY, I KNOW
YOU'RE NEW HERE,
SO I'M GOING TO CUT YOU
SOME SLACK, BUT--
"SANDY" IS MY
WHITE SLAVE NAME.
I HAVE A RIGHT
TO BE CALLED "RAVEN."
I'M RAVEN.
OKAY, MR. HAMMOND...
ON THREE. ONE...
TWO...WHY SHOULD SHE SMILE?
ISN'T HER SISTER DEAD?
HOWARD HUGHES
DIED A DERELICT, YOU KNOW.
HE HADN'T CUT
HIS FINGERNAILS
OR TOENAILS
FOR FIVE YEARS.
RICH PEOPLE
HAVE ALL THE FUN.
I SAW A PICTURE.
HE WAS NASTY.
NO, NOT WHEN
I KNEW HIM.
HE WAS QUIRKY,
BUT HANDSOME.
WHEN HOWARD HUGHES DIED,
400 PEOPLE
CLAIMED TO BE HIS HEIRS.
DID YOU GET MUCH, DAISY?
[CHUCKLING]
22 LIARS
SPLIT $2 BILLION.
$2 BILLION?
BILLION?
THAT'S-- HANG ON.
THAT'S $2 BILLION
DIVIDED BY 22 PEOPLE,
THAT EQUALS...
THAT EQUALS A FUCKLOAD
OF MONEY EACH.
GEORGE, YOU SHOULD
GO TO THE MORGUE
AND GIVE JOHN DOE
HIS NAME BACK.
TRIED THAT ALREADY.
IT DIDN'T WORK.
WELL, WE COULD BE
DISTANT RELATIONS.
HE COULD BE LOADED.
WE NEED
TO GET DOWN THERE.
I'LL GO WITH YOU.
YOU HAVE NO BUSINESS
DOWN AT THAT MORGUE.
I HAVE NO BUSINESS
DOWN AT THAT MORGUE?
ALL OF OUR BUSINESS
IS DOWN AT THAT MORGUE.
GEORGE, PLEASE
JUST DO YOUR JOB.
THOSE ARE
VERY STRONG WORDS
FOR A BOSS
WHO WENT A.W.O.L.
WHEN ARE YOU GOING TO
SHOW US THOSE SLIDES
FROM YOUR VACATION?
OR WAS IT A BUSINESS TRIP?
I THINK WE'RE DONE
TALKING ABOUT ME.
WE NEVER STARTED
TALKING ABOUT YOU.
WELL, THEN YOU'LL
HAVE TO BEGIN
WITHOUT THE BENEFIT
OF MY PARTICIPATION.
I HAVE REAL BUSINESS
TO ATTEND TO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?WHAT?
GO TO THE FUCKING MORGUE
IF YOU WANT TO.
SLIDE YOUR DEAD
DRUNKEN ASS
INTO A DRAWER
WITH SOME OTHER
DEAD DRUNK.
TAKE A NAP
IN A BODY BAG.
I DON'T CARE.
HE'S CHANGED, ISN'T HE?
YEAH. WHERE DID HE GO
ON THOSE DAYS OFF?
ROXY?
HE DIDN'T TELL ME SHIT.
ANYWAY, HE'S GONE.
GEORGE, YOU NEED TO LEARN
A FEW THINGS
ABOUT THE JOHN DOES
OF THIS WORLD--
FORGET IT.
I WORK TODAY,
AND MILLIE HAS USED UP
ALL HER EXCUSES.
SO TELL MILLIE
TO GET DOWN TO THE MORGUE
AT LUNCHTIME,
LIKE NORMAL WORKING PEOPLE.
I ACTUALLY HAVE TO
WORK TODAY, MYSELF...
DOING WHAT I WAS
MEANT TO DO.
HOOKER?[LAUGHING]
I'M ACTING.
ON A T.V. SHOW.
ARE YOU SLEEPING
WITH THE PRODUCER?
THAT'S BETWEEN ME AND HIM.
I HOPE SO.SO ARE YOU?
ARE YOU SLEEPING
WITH RAY?
GEORGE...
I'M NOT THE KIND OF GIRL
THAT LIKES TO KISS AND TELL.
SINCE WHEN?
SINCE NOW.
I'D LOVE TO SEE YOU
ACT, DAISY.
THEN YOU SHOULD COME DOWN.
RAY WOULD LOVE TO SEE YOU.
I WILL.
AND YOU, TOO, GEORGE.
I'M NOT INTERESTED.
DIDN'T CARE FOR RAY MUCH.
YEAH, RAY IS AN ASSHOLE,
ISN'T HE?
I HAVE TO GO TO WORK.
GEORGIE--
ME, YOU...
DOWN AT THE MORGUE,
MINING FOR GOLD.
GO THERE YOURSELF.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT HE LOOKS LIKE.
ALWAYS LOOKING FOR
A QUICK WAY TO MAKE A BUCK.
OKAY.
POOR MAN,
THOUGH, EH?
POOR JOHN DOE.
ANONYMOUS...
SAD.
DUST TO DUST.
WE JUST GOT
A JOHN DOE IN HERE
ABOUT 20 MINUTES AGO.
SCORE.
I JUST WANT TO WARN YOU,
SEEING A LIFELESS BODY
CAN BE VERY DIFFICULT.
THANK YOU.
THAT'S WHY
WE'RE HERE TOGETHER,
FOR EACH OTHER.
[SCREAMING]
[WAILING INCONSOLABLY]
UH... MASON?
[MASON WAILING]
MASON!
WAKE UP!
MASON!WHAT? WHAT?
[IN A BAD SOUTHERN DRAWL]
MY MISTAKE.
I'M SORRY.
MY BROTHER HERE IS JUST
IN A STATE OF SHOCK.
[DRAWLING]
WE WERE VERY CLOSE.
HE WAS LIKE
AN UNCLE TO ME.
I THOUGHT HE WAS YOUR UNCLE.
[SOBBING]
BUT SO MUCH MORE.
[GASPS]
DON'T MAKE ME LOOK AT HIM.
HOLD ME.
I CAN'T BEAR
TO SEE UNCLE ARTHUR
THIS WAY.
[SOBBING]
IT'S NOT HIM..
I KNEW THAT.
HEH...
[NORMAL VOICE]
MATE?
HOW MANY FUCKING
JOHN DOES DO YOU GOT
IN THIS FUCKING FREEZER?
FIVE.
WELL?
DO WE HAVE A WINNER?
I'M CRYING
ON THE INSIDE.
ANYWAY, DOES IT SAY THERE
IF MY UNCLE
LEFT ANY OF HIS
PERSONAL EFFECTS
AT THE SCENE?
WHAT?
IN HIS SHOPPING CART
OR HIS SLEEPING BAG?
NOTHING OF VALUE,
IF THAT'S WHAT
YOU'RE SHOOTING AT.
SHUT UP.
YOU'RE A FUCKING LIAR.
NOTHING BUT
THE CLOTHES ON HIS BACK.
[SIGHING]
ALL RIGHT THEN,
THANK YOU. BYE.
COMING, GEORGIE?
I THOUGHT
YOUR NAME WAS MILLIE.
HAGEN.
IT IS.IT IS?
I THINK I'M GOING TO
STAY A MOMENT.
SAY A PROPER GOODBYE.
IT'S NOT MY JOB
TO SAY WHO LIVES AND DIES,
AND IT SURE AS SHIT
ISN'T MY JOB
TO GIVE ANYBODY
A LITTLE DIGNITY
WHEN THEY DO.
MY JOB SUCKS.
[DOOR OPENS]
MISS HAGEN?
FUCK, THAT'S ME.
OH, YES?
IS THIS
THE CORRECT ADDRESS
TO SEND THE BILL
FOR THE BURIAL COSTS?
WHAT BURIAL COSTS?
$400.
WHY AM I GETTING
HIT WITH THIS?
YOU'RE THE NEXT OF KIN.
IF HE HAD BEEN
A JOHN DOE,
THE COUNTY WOULD ASSUME
THE COSTS, BUT HE'S NOT.
HE'S ARTHUR SIMMS.
AND HE'S GOT FAMILY.
NO... HE DOESN'T.
HE DOESN'T HAVE ANYONE.
OH, NOW I GET IT.
GENEROSITY IS FOR PEOPLE
WHO CAN AFFORD IT.
I SHOULD HAVE
SEEN THIS COMING.
I WAS ALWAYS GOOD
ON INITIAL IMPULSE.
I NEVER EARNED ANY BADGES
FOR FOLLOW-THROUGH.
GEORGIA, YOU SAID
YOU WANTED TO DO THIS.
I DID.
YOU SIGNED UP TO SELL
A HUNDRED BOXES OF COOKIES.
YOU DO IT.
WE ARE GOING OUTSIDE
TO SELL THESE COOKIES.
IT'S TOO HOT.
NOW.
IT'S TOO STRESSFUL.
WE NEED TO MOVE THESE.
I JUST WANTED
THE STUPID BADGE.
YOU CAN'T
GET THE BADGE
UNTIL YOU SELL
THE COOKIES.
SCREW THE BADGE.
GO TO YOUR ROOM.
NO DINNER FOR YOU,
YOUNG LADY.
[DAISY] THIS DOESN'T
REALLY FEEL LIKE
PROFESSIONAL ACTING, RAY.
I MEAN, WE'RE SETTING UP
IN THE BACK OF A BAR.
DAISY, THAT'S WHAT
REALITY TELEVISION IS.
WE AMBUSH.
YEAH, I'M JUST SAYING
IT'D BE NICE
TO HAVE A SET.
DAISY, WE HAVE SOMETHING
BETTER THAN A SET.
WE HAVE A BAR ROOM
FULL OF PEOPLE
WHO HAVE NO CLUE
WE'RE FILMING THEM.
ONE OF WHOM
YOU'RE GOING TO GET
TO PLAY AN ADULTERER.
TRUST ME, IT'S GOING TO FEEL
VERY MUCH LIKE ACTING.
TIGHTEN UP CAMERA TWO
FOR ME, PLEASE.
I NEED A SCRIPT.
WORDS TO COMMIT
TO MEMORY.
THAT, TO ME, IS ACTING.
OKAY, HERE'S YOUR SCRIPT--
PRETEND YOU LIKE
THE GUY...
AND GET HIM TO LIKE YOU.
HOW'S THAT?SHAKESPEAREAN.
JUST SO YOU KNOW,
I'VE BEEN IN FILMS
WITH MAJOR MOVIE STARS.
OH, I'M SURE YOU HAVE.
BUT, HEY, GUESS WHAT?
TODAY YOU'RE THE STAR.
HUH?
LAST LOOKS, PLEASE.
IS THIS A GOOD PLACE
FOR ME TO SIT?
IT'S PERFECT, SWEETHEART.
COME ON, FOLKS.
LET'S GET THIS SHOW
ON THE ROAD.
AND OUT OF THIS DUMP.
DO YOU NOT WANT TO
DO THIS, DAISY?
'CAUSE IF YOU DON'T WANT
TO DO IT, DON'T.
WE'LL JUST STOP
WHAT WE'RE DOING
AND GO HOME.
EVERYBODY? FOLKS.
SAY THE WORD.
WE'LL-- WE'LL PACK IT IN.
COME BACK ANOTHER DAY,
WITH ANOTHER GIRL.
REALLY, I CAN--
I CAN ALWAYS
GET ANOTHER GIRL.
HOW'S MY LIPSTICK?
YOU COULD USE
A LITTLE TOUCH-UP.
ALL RIGHT, FOLKS,
SHOW TIME.
[MAN] SECONDS AWAY,
PEOPLE, SECONDS AWAY.
HI, CRYSTAL.HI.
ANYTHING GOOD
IN YOUR CRYSTAL BALL?
[CHUCKLING]
"CRYSTAL BALL."
THERE'S SOMEONE
WAITING FOR YOU
IN THE CONFERENCE ROOM.
WHAT DO THEY WANT?
IT DOESN'T SAY.
HI.
MS.  HAY-GEN?
DID I SAY THAT RIGHT?
ACTUALLY, NO, IT'S "HAGEN."
AS IN "-DAZS."
I'M MICKEY.
HI, MICKEY.
WHO ARE YOU?
I RUN THE METRO SOUTH
HOMELESS SHELTER.
OH. THAT'S NICE.
OH, WELL, I CHECK ON THE GUYS
DOWN AT THE FIFTH STREET
ENCAMPMENT EVERY FEW DAYS.
THEY TOLD ME ABOUT MONTANA--
ABOUT ARTHUR SIMMS,
HIS DEATH,
AND THEN I CALLED THE CITY,
AND THAT LED ME TO YOU.
SHIT.
UH, THESE...
THESE ARE
MONTANA'S BELONGINGS.
WOW.
I WAS...
WONDERING WHERE
HIS STUFF WENT.
THANK YOU, MICKEY.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
SO YOU KNEW...
UNCLE ARTHUR?
YEAH, A LITTLE BIT.
I CERTAINLY DIDN'T KNOW
HE HAD ANY FAMILY.
WELL, WE WEREN'T
A CLOSE-KNIT CREW.
YOU KNOW, I ALWAYS WONDERED
WHY HE CALLED HIMSELF
"MONTANA".
I THINK MONTANA
LOVED THE OUTDOORS.
HE WAS A "BIG SKY"
KIND OF GUY, YOU KNOW?
I KNOW HE LOVED
A GOOD BARBECUE.
YOU DIDN'T KNOW HIM AT ALL,
DID YOU?
WE WERE PLANNING
ON GETTING TOGETHER.
WE HAD...
SCHEDULING ISSUES.
I ALWAYS WONDER
HOW MY CLIENTS
END UP WHERE THEY DO--
ON THE FRINGES, YOU KNOW?
AND THEN I RUN INTO
SOME FAMILY MEMBER
WHO DOESN'T GIVE TWO SHITS,
AND THAT'S IT,
THE MYSTERY'S SOLVED.
I GIVE A SHIT.
NOT TWO.
OH, IS THAT WHY
THE COUNTY'S TAKING
CARE OF HIM?
I JUST DON'T HAVE 400 BUCKS
LYING AROUND.
YEAH, AND SINCE YOU LEFT HIM
TO CHARITY HIS WHOLE LIFE,
WHY CHANGE NOW?
I'M SO SICK
OF YOU PEOPLE!
SHAME ON YOU.
A LITTLE HEADS-UP
ON THE DEAD, MICKEY.
PUT THEM
IN A MARBLE TEMPLE,
STICK THEM IN A COFFEE CAN,
EITHER WAY,
THEY DON'T CARE.
THEY'RE DEAD.
I'M GOING TO HELL.
OR MAYBE
I'M STAYING HERE FOREVER.
MILLIE,
WHAT WAS THAT?
OH, IT'S NOTHING, DELORES.
JUST A FAMILY THING.
MILLIE, IS HE
ASKING YOU FOR MONEY?
BECAUSE MY COUSIN, LOUIS,
TOOK ME FOR A TIDY SUM,
NEVER PAID IT BACK,
AND NOW HE LIVES
IN ECUADOR
WITH A MAN SERVANT
AND EVERYTHING--
NO, DELORES,
SOMEONE DIED.
SOMEONE CLOSE?
NO, IT'S JUST
THE MONEY'S FOR HIS BURIAL,
AND I DON'T HAVE IT.
HOW MUCH?$400.
WELL, SILLY,
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS ASK.
FAMILY EMERGENCY.
THAT'S WHAT ADVANCES
ARE FOR, MILLIE.
I'LL GET A CHECK CUT FOR YOU
RIGHT AWAY.
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU CARED SO MUCH.
NEITHER DID I.
HEY, J.D.
LOOK WHO'S HERE.
I DON'T DO
PREPPY DOGS.
WELL, HE'S NOT PREPPY.
HE IS.
GET HIM
AWAY FROM ME.
MOM! COME GET J.D.
REGGIE, YOU DON'T
NEED TO SHOUT.
I'M RIGHT HERE.
HELLO.
GUESS YOU DON'T
REMEMBER ME,
MRS. LASS?
OH, MY GOD...
SANDY SIMONS, IS THAT YOU
UNDER ALL THAT EYELINER?
IN THE FLESH.
OH, I HEARD
YOU MOVED BACK TO TOWN.
HOW'S YOUR MOM?DIVORCED.
I'M SORRY TO HEAR THAT.
DON'T BE.
MY DAD'S A FREAK.
COME ON, REGGIE.
LET'S GO ONLINE.
SO, SANDY...
WHERE DID YOU
DISCOVER THIS...
NEW LOOK?
FLORIDA.
MY NAME'S "RAVEN" NOW.
NICE.
MOM, CAN YOU
TAKE J.D., PLEASE?
WHY? DON'T YOU WANT HIM
WITH YOU?
NO. HE'S TOO PREPPY.
PREPPY?
FINE.
DO YOU GIRLS
WANT SOMETHING
TO EAT?
SOMETHING SWEET.
UH, DO YOU HAVE
ANY CHARCOAL?
NO. NO, NO, GIRLS.
I'M SORRY, NO MATCHES.
CHARCOAL EYELINER.
I'M GOING TO DO
REGGIE'S MAKE-UP.
OH!
SURE.
I'LL GET IT.
[J.D. WHIMPERS]
OH, DON'T YOU WORRY.
SHE NEEDS A FRIEND
WHO'S HUMAN.
OR SOMETHING CLOSE.
SAY IT AIN'T SO.
OH, BROTHER.
TRULY STUNNING WORK,
YOUNG REMBRANDT.
WHAT'D YOU CALL ME,
ASSHOLE?
CHRIST.
I WAS HOPING TO PAY TRIBUTE
TO YOUR ARTWORK.
WELL, I THINK IT'S SHIT.
ALWAYS STRIVING.
ALWAYS PUSHING
TO MAKE YOUR WORK
A CUT ABOVE.
I APPRECIATE THAT
IN A YOUNG PERSON.
IN FACT, I'D LOVE
TO SHAKE YOUR HAND.
START CLIMBING THEN, GRANDPA.
HOW ABOUT YOU COME DOWN?
THE CLIMB UP
IS HALF THE EXPERIENCE.
FALLING DOWN THE OTHER HALF?
MAYBE FOR YOU.
I NEVER FALL.
EVER.
I WANT TO PAY YOU
FOR YOUR WORK.
CALL IT
ART APPRECIATION.
HOW ABOUT, SAY...
30 BUCKS?
CASH ON THE BARREL HEAD,
IF YOU COME DOWN
IN THE NEXT TWO MINUTES.
YOU MEDICI MOTHERFUCKER.
YOU CAN'T RUSH ART.
I'LL MAKE IT 40.
$40 FOR AN ORIGINAL WORK
BY THE GREAT "B. BOYD."
WHAT THE FUCK?
I AIN'T THAT HACK, MAN.
I'M UP HERE
BLOTTING HIS SHIT OUT.
WHAT THE FUCK, INDEED.
GET THE FUCK OUT
OF MY AIRSPACE, MOTHERFUCKER,
BEFORE I SHOOT YOU DOWN!
TERRIBLE, WHAT PEOPLE DO
TO OTHER PEOPLE'S PROPERTY.
SHIT! HEADS UP!
TAG.
YOU'RE IT.
B-BOY! B-BOY,
GET UP, MAN!
GET UP!
DAMN, LOOK AT
THAT PATTERN.
WATCH YOUR STEP NOW.
I HAVE TO SAY
I'M A LITTLE NERVOUS
ABOUT THIS.
THERE'S NOTHING
TO BE NERVOUS ABOUT.
I JUST FEEL LIKE
IT'S UNDERHANDED,
FILMING A GUY
WHO'S CHEATING HIS WIFE.
HEY, HEY, HEY...
HIS WIFE'S THE ONE
THAT CONTACTED US.
SHE THINKS THIS IS
WHERE HE COMES
TO PICK UP WOMEN.
DON'T MAKE ME OUT
TO BE THE BAD GUY.
I'M NOT.
SO HOW DO I LOOK?
GOOD ENOUGH
TO END A MARRIAGE.
WHERE ARE THE CAMERAS?
THERE. THERE.
THERE AND THERE.
ANY MORE QUESTIONS?
NO. YOU?
YEAH.
ARE YOU SURE YOU KNOW
HOW TO SEDUCE A MAN?
I DON'T KNOW.
DO I?
WE'LL SEE.
EVERYTHING PINK GOES?
BURN IT.
IS THAT HER?
YEAH. THAT'S MY SISTER.
IT'S THE ONLY
YEARBOOK PICTURE OF HER
I EVER FOUND.
SHE WAS TOO COOL
FOR THAT BULLSHIT.
SHE WAS NEVER
IN ANY CLUBS OR ANYTHING.
NOT BEING IN STUFF
IS COOL.
NOT LIKE MY SISTER,
PRESIDENT OF THE "MY SHIT
DOESN'T STINK SOCIETY."
CAN I SEE HER ROOM?
[DOOR OPENS]YOUR ORDER, LADIES.
LOOKS GOOD, REGGIE.
THANKS.
HER NAME'S
NOT "REGGIE" ANYMORE.
DARE I ASK?
IT'S "SPIDER".
SPIDER, HUH?
THAT'S PRETTY.
UM, YOU KNOW,
WE DON'T HAVE A LOT OF
SWEETS IN THE HOUSE,
BUT I DID FIND THESE.
I THINK THOSE ARE
REALLY STALE.
THAT'S OKAY,
I LIKE STALE.
IT'S CLOSER TO DEATH.
WELL, TRY NOT TO GET
A LOT OF CRUMBS
ON THE FLOOR.
SO, UM, WELL,
YOU GIRLS, HAVE FUN.
UM, WOULD YOU
LIKE TO ASK RAVEN OVER
FOR DINNER... SPIDER?
SURE.TERRIFIC.
CAN WE INVITE
A COUPLE OF FRIENDS?
OF COURSE. YEAH.
CAN WE HAVE PIZZA?
PIZZA IT IS.
YOUR MOM'S COOL.
NOT REALLY.
COME HERE MUCH?
ISN'T THAT
SUPPOSED TO BE
A MAN'S LINE?
I DIDN'T KNOW
THERE WAS A SCRIPT.
WANT TO HEAR MY GUESS
ABOUT YOU, WALTER?
UH-OH... NOW
I'M GETTING NERVOUS.
ANOTHER SHOT OF COURAGE,
MY FRIEND?
THANK YOU.
HOW ABOUT YOU, MISS?NO, I'M GOOD.
WELL, THAT'S GOOD TO KNOW.
MY GUESS, WALTER,
IS THAT YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE AT HOME RIGHT NOW,
BUT YOU WORK A LONG DAY,
AND THE WIFE ISN'T ALWAYS
A WELCOME FACE
AT THE END OF IT.
I SHOULD GET GOING.
YOU HAVE A NICE NECK.
IT'S STRONG.
DOES YOUR WIFE
KISS YOUR NECK, WALTER?
SHE SHOULD.
JESUS.JESUS.
I'M SORRY.
I'M MAKING YOU
UNCOMFORTABLE.
YOU'RE THE KIND OF GUY
THAT BELIEVES IN STAYING
WITH SOMEBODY FOREVER.
I GAVE UP ON FOREVER.
IT DOESN'T LAST.
I'M A BIG FAN OF JUST
ONE REALLY GOOD NIGHT.
ARE YOU A GOOD KISSER,
WALTER?
UM...
I DON'T KNOW.
I BET YOU WOULD BE.
I'M SORRY.
I'M NOT A CHEATER.
YOU'RE NOT, ARE YOU?
NO.
TOP YOU UP THERE, PAL?
I'M FINE.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
WATCH MY BAG?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HE DOESN'T WANT TO CHEAT.
REALLY? HOW DO YOU
KNOW THAT?
BECAUSE HE SAID SO.
MEN SAY A LOT
OF FUCKING THINGS, DAISY,
ALL DAY LONG,
BUT MOSTLY AT NIGHT.
OR MAYBE
YOU DON'T KNOW MEN.
I KNOW MEN FINE.
THIS GUY IS CLUELESS.
HE WANTS TO BE TOLD
WHAT TO DO.
WHAT HE WANTS.
WHAT DOES HE WANT?
HE WANTS
WHAT WE ALL WANT.
HE WANTS TO FEEL ALIVE.
RIGHT, DAISY?
I DON'T KNOW.
HE'S NOT A CHEATER,
I CAN SEE IT.
SO WHAT ARE YOU,
A FUCKING MARRIAGE
COUNSELOR NOW?
NO.NO.
YOU'RE AN ACTRESS.
ACT LIKE YOU WANT TO
MAKE HIM HAPPY.
MAKE ME HAPPY.
FINE.
AM I BEING HARD ON YOU?YES.
I'M AN AWFUL GUY.
I'M MEAN. I'M TERRIBLE.
YOU REALLY ARE.
I REALLY AM.
NOW GO OUT THERE...
AND SHOW HIM NO MERCY.
ALL RIGHT?MM.
ALL RIGHT, MILLIE.
HERE YOU GO. $400.
THANK YOU, DELORES.
FOR YOUR UNCLE'S BURIAL.
UNCLE ARTHUR, WAS IT?RIGHT.
THE GOOD NEWS
WAS I HAD A CHECK
FOR 400 BUCKS.
THE BAD NEWS WAS...
I WAS THINKING ABOUT
KEEPING THE MONEY.
THIS IS A SWEET THING
YOU'RE DOING--
WORKING OVERTIME
TO PAY HIM TRIBUTE.
THAT'S WHAT WE DO
FOR FAMILY, I GUESS.
I WAS WORKING FOR IT,
SO WHY SHOULD I
SPEND IT ON SOME GUY
JUST BECAUSE HE'S DEAD?
I'M DEAD, TOO.
HONORING THE DEAD
HELPS US GO ON LIVING.
I KNOW.
ONE HOT LEATHER JACKET,
AND NO ONE WOULD BE
THE WISER.
THE THING THAT'S LOVELY
ABOUT THIS GESTURE
IS THAT YOU'RE NOT JUST
LOOKING FOR A PAT
ON THE BACK.
ON MY HOT NEW
LEATHER JACKET.
RIGHT.
THAT'S THE WAY I FEEL
ABOUT MY KIDS.
WHAT KIDS?
THE LITTLE ONES I SPONSOR.
OH!
SAY HELLO TO...
KASAWALA.
AND ANJALI.
AND...
THIS IS CHING-ZI.
I SAW HER PICTURE
IN MY SUNDAY PARADE,
AND I JUST COULDN'T RESIST
ADDING ONE MORE.
AND THIS...
I'M NOT SUPPOSED
TO PLAY FAVORITES.
THIS IS FALLANDA.
ISN'T SHE BEAUTIFUL?
$15 A MONTH
FROM YOURS TRULY
GETS HER
A MONTHLY SUPPLY
OF HIGH-PROTEIN LUNCHES,
AND HER VILLAGE
GETS A WATER PUMP.
THAT'S SO SWEET, DELORES.
OH.
I MEAN, SHE'LL NEVER
THANK ME IN PERSON,
BUT THAT'S NOT
WHAT'S IMPORTANT,
AS YOU KNOW.
THANK YOU, DELORES HERBIG,
AND YOUR BIG, BROWN EYES.
RIGHT.
THE IMPORTANT THING IS
WHEN LIFE PRESENTS US
WITH AN OPPORTUNITY
TO HELP SOMEONE
WHO CAN'T HELP THEMSELVES,
WE HAVE TO STEP UP,
AND THAT'S WHAT
YOU'RE DOING RIGHT NOW.
AND JUST LIKE THAT,
I LOST MY HOT NEW
LEATHER JACKET.
THANK YOU
FOR THE FINE EXAMPLE
YOU SET.
HEY... THIS IS NICE.
I LOST MY OTHER JACKET
WHEN I DIED.
THANK YOU, GEORGIA LASS.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
PRETTY GIRL
YOU WERE TALKING TO.
SEEMS NICE.
OH, I DON'T THINK SO.
I DON'T THINK
THAT ONE'S SO NICE.
WELL, YOU NEVER KNOW.
WOULDN'T YOU JUST KILL
TO FIND OUT, THOUGH?
GOD, I KNOW I WOULD.
EXCUSE ME.
GOOD EVENING, SIR.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I'VE COME TO SEE DAISY ACT.
WHERE ARE THE CAMERAS?
THEY'RE HIDDEN,
AND SHUT THE FUCK UP.
EXCUSE ME?SHUT THE FUCK UP.
AND DON'T TALK TO HER.
FINE.
THE ONLY REASON
YOU HAVE TO OPEN YOUR MOUTH
IS TO POUR BOOZE IN IT.
AND WHAT ARE WE
DRINKING TO, RAY?
THEY'RE BOTH FOR YOU.
LOOKING GOOD, DAISY.NOT NOW, MASON.
I'M NOT GOING
TO FUCKING TELL YOU AGAIN.
WELL, LOOK
WHO'S STILL HERE.
YOU ASKED ME
TO WATCH YOUR BAG.
OH.
LUCKY ME.
I FOUND A BOY SCOUT.
OKAY, GO HOME,
BOY SCOUT.
YOU DID YOUR GOOD DEED.
YOU KNOW WHAT EVERYBODY SAYS
ON THEIR DEATHBED, WALTER?
THEY WISH THEY'D HAD
MORE FUN.
AND MEN WISH
THEY'D HAD MORE WOMEN.
FIVE REASONS
MEN COME
TO A BAR, WALTER.
ONE...
THEY DON'T LOVE
THEIR WIFE ANYMORE.
TWO, THEIR WIFE
DOESN'T LOVE THEM.
THREE, THEY WANT TO SEE
WHAT THEY'RE MISSING.
AND FOUR,
THEY WANT,
IF JUST FOR A MOMENT,
TO TASTE IT.
FIVE...
MAYBE THERE WERE JUST FOUR.
YOU WANT TO GO SOMEWHERE
WITH ME, WALTER?
I DO.
BLACKSTONE HOTEL.
GET US A ROOM.
I'LL FOLLOW.
NOW?NOW.
UM, I HAVE TO PAY
MY BAR TAB.
NO, I GOT IT.
GO THE HOTEL,
BOY SCOUT.
HOW'S THAT FOR NO MERCY?
JIMMY,
BLACKSTONE HOTEL, NOW.
I'M NOT GOING THERE.
NO, YOU'RE NOT,
THOUGH IT SURE SEEMED
LIKE YOU WANTED TO.
WHAT THE FUCK
WAS THAT KISS?
I WAS JUST
PLAYING THE PART, RAY,
GOING WITH IT.
A LITTLE TOO WELL.
YOU'RE HURTING ME.
WELL, MAYBE I'M JUST
PLAYING THE PART
OF THE JEALOUS BOYFRIEND.
[SIGHS]
I'M SORRY.
SEE? SEE WHAT YOU DO TO ME?
YOU ARE
A HELL OF AN ACTRESS.
THANK YOU.
COME HERE.
I'LL SEE YOU
LATER TONIGHT?OKAY.
GOOD SEEING
YOU, MASON.
WHAT WAS THAT?I WAS ACTING.
ACTING LIKE WHAT,
A WHORE?
BECAUSE IT WAS
BLOODY BRILLIANT,
DEFINITIVE.
YOU'RE DRUNK, MASON,
AND YOU SMELL.
YOU SMELL.
HE SMELLS. THIS WHOLE
BLOODY THING SMELLS.
GO HOME.
I JUST WANTED TO SAY
YOU WERE REALLY GREAT.
THANK YOU.
IT'S REALLY NICE OF YOU
TO COME UP
AND TELL ME THAT.
I KNOW SOME PEOPLE ARE SHY
ABOUT APPROACHING ACTORS,
BUT IT REALLY MAKES MY DAY.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
MELISSA. I'M HIS WIFE.
OH."OH?"
THAT'S IT?
THAT'S ALL I GET?
THAT'S ALL YOU HAVE LEFT?
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WOULD BE HERE.
THEY DIDN'T TELL ME.
OKAY. LET'S BLAME THEM.
[GIRL]
SO SHE'S DEAD?
I'M DEAD.
READY?
SPEAK TO THE SPIRITS.
"LIGHT AS A FEATHER,
STIFF AS A BOARD."
STIFF AS A BOARD.
LIGHT AS A FEATHER,
STIFF AS A BOARD."
SORRY TO INTERRUPT, GIRLS.
JUST THOUGHT
I'D BRING IN SOME SODAS.
MOM.
THAT'S COOL,
MRS. LASS.
THANKS.
WOULD YOU LIKE
TO PLAY A GAME?
NO WAY.
WHAT ARE YOU PLAYING?
NOTHING.REGGIE...
CHILL OUT.
YOUR MOM IS COOL.
UM, WHY DON'T YOU GIRLS
LEVITATE WITHOUT ME?
"LIGHT AS A FEATHER,
STIFF AS A BOARD."
WOW. AREN'T YOU...
I MEAN...AREN'T I WHAT?
YOU LOOK GOOD.
THANK YOU.
I'M GOING TO GO TAKE A PEEK.
IF SHE SEES YOU,
SHE'LL FREAK.
THANKS FOR INVITING ME.
IF YOU GET CAUGHT,
I KNOW NOTHING.
SO WHAT EXACTLY IS "GOTH"?
DAD! YOU'RE NOT
SUPPOSED TO BE HERE.
NO BOYS ALLOWED.
REGGIE?WHAT?
WE'RE EATING
IN THE LIVING ROOM.
UH, REGGIE--
I THINK THE GREASY FOOD
SHOULD STAY IN THE KITCHEN.
MOM, DON'T EMBARRASS ME.
DAD, GET OUT!
WHAT THE HELL, JOY?
A FEW SIMPLE
SACRIFICES TO THE DEVIL,
FOLLOWED BY PIZZA.
I'M NOT COMFORTABLE
WITH THIS.
IT'S HARMLESS,
ALL RIGHT? A PHASE.
HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
I'M NOT IN LOVE WITH IT,
BUT IT'S
AN ACTUAL PARTY, CLANCY.
WITH ACTUAL FRIENDS.
REGGIE HAS FRIENDS?
REGGIE HAS FRIENDS.
WOW. LOOK WHO'S BACK.
STILL PANNING FOR GOLD
IN DRY GULCH?
NO.
SO WHAT'S THE SAD STORY
THIS TIME?
I THINK
YOU'LL LIKE THIS ONE.
ONCE UPON A TIME,
THERE WERE THESE FOUR GUYS
NAMED BENJAMIN,
AND THEY COULD HAVE
TURNED INTO
A NICE LEATHER JACKET,
BUT INSTEAD,
THEY ENDED UP
ON YOUR CRUMMY DESK.
I THOUGHT ARTHUR SIMMS
DIDN'T HAVE A FAMILY.
HE DOES NOW.
COMPLICATED GUY.
CAN I JUST HAVE
A RECEIPT, PLEASE?
ONE SECOND.
NICE FROG.
THAT'S GENERAL TSAO.
AND THIS...
IS ARTHUR SIMMS.
YOU'RE SHITTING ME?
WHAT'D YOU THINK
YOU WERE GETTING FOR $400?
A GRAVE. A HEADSTONE.
THE CITY HASN'T HAD FUNERALS
FOR TRANSIENTS FOR YEARS.
WE BURN THEM.
THERE'S A LANDFILL
OVER BY THE FREEWAY--
YEAH, I GET IT.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU PAID FOR THEM,
THEY'RE YOURS.
WHAT THE FUCK
DO I WANT THEM FOR?
ASHES HAVE MANY USES.
ALL KINDS OF THINGS
YOU CAN DO WITH PEOPLE.
DON'T TRY TO PLAY
CREEPY DEATH GUY WITH ME.
I SEE DEATH ALL THE TIME.
WELL, YOU MAY SEE DEATH
ALL THE TIME, SWEETHEART,
BUT YOU OBVIOUSLY
DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO WITH IT.
AND THIS ONE'S YOURS.
ALL RIGHT. FINE.
NOT VERY HEAVY
FOR A WHOLE DEAD GUY.
ASHES TO ASHES.
BUT YOU KNOW
ALL ABOUT THAT,
DON'T YOU?
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
MM.
OKAY, SO TELL ME
THE RULES.
YEAH, ME TOO.
WE'LL JUST GO
AROUND THE CIRCLE
UNTIL YOU GET IT,
THEN YOU CAN JOIN IN.
DON'T EMBARRASS ME.
TABITHA... GO.
OVERDOSE.
OF WHAT?
ASPIRIN.BORING.
OKAY, WAIT.
BOILING OIL.
BOILING ACID.
ELECTROCUTION.
DECAPITATION.
FLAYING.
BRAIN EMBOLISM.
CARPAL TUNNEL.
WHAT'S THAT?
IT'S REALLY, REALLY BAD.
OKAY. MRS. LASS?
UM, WELL...
IN MY SLEEP,
AGE 98,
SURROUNDED BY FLOWERS...
AND GRANDCHILDREN...
AND ALL THE PEOPLE I LOVE.
JESUS, MOM, THAT'S NOT
HOW YOU PLAY THE GAME.
WELL, THAT'S MY ANSWER.
THAT'S OKAY, REGGIE.
YOU GO.
OKAY...
I'M KILLED...
BY A TOILET SEAT
THAT FALLS
FROM A SPACE STATION,
AND I'M BLOWN TO BITS.
WOW.
OKAY, PARTY'S OVER.
TIME TO GO.
BUT MY MOM CAN'T
PICK ME UP UNTIL LATER.
I SAID IT'S TIME TO GO.
MOM.COME ON, GIRLS. NOW.
CALL YOUR PARENTS.
MRS. LASS,
I TOTALLY THINK
YOU'RE OVERREACTING.
SANDY,
I THINK YOU NEED
TO GO UPSTAIRS
AND GET YOUR THINGS
AND GO HOME,
AND PUT SOME COLD CREAM
ON YOUR FACE,
AND FOLLOW IT UP
WITH SOME ASTRINGENT, HUH?
'CAUSE THAT PANCAKE MAKEUP
IS GOING TO DESTROY
YOUR SKIN.
YOU DON'T WANT TO GET
ACNE SCARS.
SO MEAN!
THANKS A LOT.
YOUR SISTER'S DEATH
IS NOT A GAME.
WHATEVER.
I'M SORRY, REGGIE,
BUT I'M NOT COMFORTABLE--
WHO'S THAT?
SAY HELLO
TO ARTHUR SIMMS.
HE'S HAD QUITE A DAY.
YEAH.
HEY, KIFFCOFFEE?
NO, I'M GOOD.
IS THAT
SOMEONE'S ASHES?
NO. NO WAY.
DON'T PUT SOMEONE'S ASHES
ON MY TABLE.
IT'S BAD LUCK.
HE WOKE UP
THIS MORNING
LIFE-SIZE...
NOW LOOK AT HIM.
NO HEADSTONE.
NO NOTHING.
YOU DON'T NEED
A HEADSTONE
IF NOBODY'S GOING TO
COME TO SEE IT.
ARE THOSE ASHES?
YES.
I WAS CREMATED,
YOU KNOW.
YOU BURNED TO DEATH.
THAT'S WHAT I JUST SAID.
GONE WITH THE WIND...
ON  GONE WITH THE WIND.
I DIDN'T FIND THAT FUNNY.
I DID.
HOW'D YOUR BIG DAY GO?
PERFECT.
I NAILED EVERY SCENE.
REALLY?APPARENTLY, I'M A VERY
GIFTED ACTRESS.
REALLY?
ASK MASON.
HE WAS THERE.
WHAT'S THAT?ARTHUR SIMMS.
WHO'S THAT?UNCLE ARTHUR.
UNCLE ARTHUR!
YOU'VE LOST WEIGHT.
CHEERS. CHEERS.
CHEERS.
SO, MASON, WAS DAISY
A GOOD ACTRESS?
YES, SHE IS.THANK YOU.
ALWAYS HAS BEEN,
IT TURNS OUT.
MY EYES HAVE BEEN OPENED.
MY EARS HAVE HEARD
THAT WHICH THEY THOUGHT
THEY NEVER WOULD.
ALL RIGHT, MASON.
WELL, LITTLE
MISS MOVIE STAR,
WE FINALLY GOT SOMEONE
THAT'S SOMEBODY.
MM. YES, I AM.
AND THAT SOMEBODY
SHOULD PICK UP THE CHECK.
UH, ROXY?
CAN YOU DO ME
ONE MORE BIG FAVOR?
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE
WITH THAT DEAD MAN.
IT'S A HEALTH CODE
VIOLATION.
CIRCLE OF LIFE,
RIGHT?
OKAY, BUT YOU HAVE TO GO
ON MY SHIFT WITH ME.
AND HE SITS
IN THE BACK SEAT.
THAT'S FINE.
CONGRATULATIONS, DAISY.
THANK YOU.
YOU KEEP DOING THAT,
YOU KNOW.
WHAT?FIXING YOUR FACE.
A GIRL'S GOT TO LOOK GOOD
FOR HER MAN.
THAT MAN GRABBED YOU
BY THE ARM, DAISY.
I DON'T THINK
I CARE FOR HIM MUCH.
WHAT YOU DON'T CARE FOR
IS THAT HE'S DATING ME.
I'D REALLY APPRECIATE IT
IF YOU'D BE CIVILIZED
WHEN HE SHOWS UP.
HE'S COMING HERE?YEP. OF COURSE.
RUBE WOULDN'T LIKE THAT.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
RUBE WOULDN'T LIKE THAT,
BUT HE'S NOT HERE,
AND YOU STILL ARE.
YOU'RE SO BEAUTIFUL.
AND I LOVE YOU.
I JUST DON'T
LIKE YOU ANYMORE.
IN A LIFETIME,
WE GET TO BE MANY THINGS.
RICH MAN, POOR MAN,
BEGGAR MAN, THIEF...
DOCTOR, LAWYER,
INDIAN CHIEF.
DAUGHTER, SISTER, SCOUT,
COLLEGE DROPOUT,
FRIEND,
DEAD GIRL...
OR MAYBE
WE JUST PLAY THE PARTS
FOR A COUPLE OF HOURS
UNTIL THE CURTAIN FALLS.
FROM THE MOMENT I MET HIM,
I KNEW SOMETHING
ABOUT ARTHUR SIMMS
WAS FAMILIAR.
I UNDERSTOOD
WANTING TO DISAPPEAR.
I WANTED TO MY WHOLE LIFE.
AND THEN I DID.
OKAY, ARTHUR SIMMS,
HERE YOU GO.
YOU LIVED,
AND THEN YOU DIED.
YOU HAVE NOT BEEN FORGOTTEN.
[♪♪]
I COULD USE
SOME BREAKFAST.
YOU HUNGRY?
I COULD EAT.
FEELS LIKE
AN OATMEAL MORNING.
HMM.
MAYBE I'LL TRY
SOMETHING DIFFERENT TODAY.
YOU SHOULD.
IT'S A BIG MENU.
YEAH...