[GRUNTING]
HE'S DEAD.
DARLING,
THERE'S NO POST-IT.
[SCREECHES]
I'M HERE TO
PICK UP A PACKAGE.
THIS HAS BEEN
IN THE DEAD LETTER OFFICE
FOR A WHILE.
WHY DIDN'T THIS
GET TO WHERE IT WAS GOING?
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED, SIR.
I WASN'T THERE.
THIS IS ALMOST
80 YEARS OLD.
[WOMAN]:
SO WHO IS THIS ROSIE?
OH, NOBODY YOU KNOW.
IS SHE RELATED TO YOU?
YES.
I SENT SOMETHING TO SOMEONE
A LONG TIME AGO,
AND IT DIDN'T GET
TO THAT SOMEONE,
AND I'M TRYING TO DO
A LITTLE FOLLOW-UP.
[ROXY]: WERE YOU DEAD
WHEN YOU SENT IT?
YES.
REALLY.
J.D., WHERE ARE YOU?
J.D.?
I WANT MOM.
[SNIFFLES]SHE'LL BE BACK SOON.
SHE'S GOING TO KILL ME.
[SCREECHES]
WHAT IS THAT?GO AWAY!
RAY, GO AWAY.
[♪♪]
[GEORGE]:  ASK MOST KIDS
WHAT THEIR FAVORITE GAME IS,
THEY'LL PROBABLY SAY
HIDE-AND-GO-SEEK.
I KNOW I LOVED IT.
ONE MISSISSIPPI.
TWO MISSISSIPPI...
FOR MOST KIDS,
THE FUN OF THE GAME
ISN'T IN THE HIDING.
THE FUN IS IN BEING FOUND.
FIVE MISSISSIPPI,
SIX MISSISSIPPI. BUT NOT FOR ME.
I DIDN'T WANT TO BE FOUND.
HERE I COME!
EVER.
GOT YOU.[GIGGLING]
THEY'LL NEVER FIND ME.
AND THEY NEVER WOULD.
ONE MISSISSIPPI.
TWO MISSISSIPPI...
THREE MISSISSIPPI, FOUR.
DADDY'S FUNNY.
IT'S ALMOST TIME
FOR BED, ROSIE.
BUT I'M HIDING,
AND YOU CAN'T FIND ME.
[GASPS]
[GEORGE]:  GOT YOU.
MORNING, KIFFANY.MORNING.
OATMEAL WITH RAISINS?
I'M OVER THE OATMEAL.
NO MORE OATMEAL.
HAVING A LOOK
AT THE MENU FOR ONCE.
AM I THE FIRST ONE HERE?
NO, ONE OF YOU NEVER LEFT.
MAMA?STAY OUT
OF THE KITCHEN.
DON'T LET ME CATCH HIM
SLEEPING BACK THERE AGAIN.
IT'S UNSANITARY.
WOW.
I HAD THIS DREAM LAST NIGHT
ABOUT WAFFLES,
AND IT WAS REALLY HORRIBLE
BECAUSE I WAS BEING CHASED
BY A BIG BUTTER PAT,
AND I COULDN'T GET ANYWHERE
BECAUSE I WAS WAIST-HIGH
IN MAPLE SYRUP.
DID YOU REALLY
SLEEP HERE LAST NIGHT?
YEAH, IT'S QUITE
COMFORTABLE, ACTUALLY.
THE SUPPLE LINOLEUM
IS QUITE NICE.
CAN I HAVE SOME PANCAKES?
IF I CAN SEE SOME MONEY.
I'LL... COVER HIM.
OOH, IN THAT CASE,
I'LL HAVE SOME BACON AS WELL,
NOT TOO CRISPY.
NOT TOO CHEWY.
JUST IN-BETWEEN.
WHY ARE YOU SLEEPING HERE?
I TOLD YOU
YOU COULD STAY WITH US.
SHE SAID I COULDN'T.
OH, REALLY?
SHE SAID THAT SHE DOESN'T
WANT ME IN YOUR HOUSE,
AND SHE WANTS NOTHING MORE
TO DO WITH ME EVER.
I NEVER SAID THAT.
WHAT I SAID WAS
I DON'T THINK IT'S WISE
FOR YOU TO LIVE WITH US.
SINCE WHEN HAVE I GIVEN
A FUCK ABOUT WISE?
LET ME MAKE THIS
STUNNINGLY SIMPLE FOR YOU.
YOU CAN'T LIVE WITH US.
OKAY. I'LL LIVE HERE.
I'M GOING TO PUT THE "HAUS"
BACK IN DER WAFFLE HAUS,
AND I'M GOING TO SLEEP
RIGHT HERE,
ON THIS LOVELY BIT
OF NAUGAHYDE.
[RUBE]:
YOU CAN'T SLEEP HERE.
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE
IT'S A PLACE OF BUSINESS,
FOR THEM AND FOR US.
YOU DON'T SLEEP
IN YOUR OFFICE, DO YOU?
I'VE SLEPT
IN MY OFFICE.
REALLY
SOUND SLEEP TOO.
DROOL ALL OVER
MY KEYBOARD.
WAKE UP,
GOT NO FUCKING IDEA
WHERE I AM.
LOOK...
I DON'T MEAN TO BE RUDE,
BUT I'D LIKE TO BE
LEFT ALONE.
MEANING?
PLEASE LEAVE.
I'VE JUST ORDERED BREAKFAST.
WELL, GET IT TO GO. PLEASE.
I LIKE YOUR TOP.
IT'S VERY STYLISH.
MEN DON'T WEAR TOPS.
THEY WEAR SHIRTS.
[MASON]:
"I LIKE YOUR TOP"?
WHAT THE FUCK WAS THAT?
[DAISY]: I WAS JUST
TRYING TO BE NICE.
IF YOU REALLY
WANTED TO BE NICE,
DAISY, YOU WOULD
TAKE IN A BOARDER.
YOU KNOW WHAT, MASON?
I AM NICE TO YOU,
AND I WANT TO CONTINUE
TO BE NICE TO YOU,
WHICH IS WHY
YOU CANNOT LIVE WITH US,
AND DON'T YOU MAKE PROMISES
ABOUT OUR HOUSE
WITHOUT CONSULTING
WITH ME FIRST.FINE.
OKAY, JUST SO WE'RE CLEAR,
THAT WAS MY HOUSE
BEFORE I GAVE IT TO YOU.
[GEORGE]:
JUST SO WE'RE CLEAR,
THAT WAS
SOME OLD DEAD WOMAN'S HOUSE
BEFORE YOU STOLE IT.
KEEP OUT OF IT, GEORGIE.
FINE.
THINGS HAVE CHANGED, MASON.
GREAT, THAT'S PERFECT.
SO I'M ON THE STREET.
THAT'S IT, THEN.
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
THINGS CHANGE.
MASON, MASON, MASON.
PENNY, MY DARLING,
HOW ARE YOU?
SO GOOD TO SEE YOU.
THIS IS GEO--HI, GEORGE.
HOW DO YOU GUYS
KNOW EACH OTHER?
[KIFFANY]:
HEY...
LONG TIME NO SEE.
WHAT BRINGS YOU HERE?
I'M HERE TO SEE THE MAN.
[GEORGE]:
ALL ROADS LEAD TO RUBE.
FLAPJACKS, $7.95.
KEEP IT.OH, THANK YOU.
NICE SEEING YOU, SWEETHEART.
YOU TOO.
SO YOU WERE PART OF
RUBE'S LITTLE POST-IT SQUAD?
I WAS, LONG BEFORE POST-ITS
WERE IN VOGUE.
SO I TAKE IT
YOU'VE BEEN DEAD A WHILE.
THAT DEPENDS.
ON?
WHAT YOU THINK A WHILE IS.
PENNY'S BEEN DEAD
FOREVER AND A DAY.
HOW'D YOU DIE?
BOATING ACCIDENT.
SAILING? WATER-SKIING?
FALL OUT OF A DINGHY?
BIGGER.
MASON...
YOU OWE ME 200 BUCKS.
DO-- REALLY, DO I?
YOU DO.
A BET'S A BET.
YEAH.HMM.
NICE TO SEE YOU, GEORGE.
WHAT WAS THE BET?
THE BET WAS...
WE HAD TO GUESS
WHAT YEAR RUBE DIED.
WHOEVER WON
GOT THE TWO HUNDRED.
WHAT WAS YOUR GUESS?
I HAVE NO IDEA,
AND IT WAS 30 YEARS AGO,
SO I'M NOT PAYING.
1927.
NOW SOMEONE OWES ME
200 BUCKS.
HEY, REG,
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
FINE.
DO YOU WANT SOME OATMEAL
WITH RAISINS?
I'M SICK OF OATMEAL.
NO MORE OATMEAL.
THEN WHY DON'T YOU
TAKE A BREAKFAST BAR.
THERE'S MAPLE.
THERE'S CRANBERRY.
THERE'S MAPLE CRANBERRY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
SWEETIE, I KNOW
THIS IS HARD,
BUT I HAVE TO PACK AWAY
ALL OF J.D.'s THINGS.
NO, YOU DON'T.
YOU'RE RIGHT, I DON'T,
BUT I WANT TO.
I THINK IT'S BEST.
I DON'T.
WE ALL MISS J.D...
VERY MUCH.
THEN WHY ARE YOU
THROWING AWAY HIS SHIT?
YOU KNOW, REGGIE,
ALL THE QUALITIES YOU COULD
INHERIT FROM YOUR SISTER,
DOES FOUL LANGUAGE
NEED TO BE ONE OF THEM?
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
I'M NOT THROWING AWAY
ANYTHING.
I'M LABELING AND STORING
HIS THINGS
SO THAT MAYBE,
WHEN WE'RE READY,
WE COULD GET
ANOTHER DOG.
WHAT IF J.D. COMES BACK?
SWEETIE, HE'S NOT.
MAYBE IT WASN'T HIM.
I DIDN'T EVEN LOOK
AT THAT DOG VERY LONG
AFTER IT HAPPENED.
HONEY.WHAT COLOR IS GEORGE?
WHAT?
WHAT COLOR DID YOU
LABEL GEORGE'S STUFF?
I DON'T REMEMBER.
THE SHIT YOU DIDN'T SELL
IN THE YARD SALE.
WE NEED TO ACCEPT
THAT J.D.'s GONE, SWEETIE.
I'M GIVING J.F. A BATH.
WHO'S J.F.?
THE FROG GEORGE LEFT ME.
REGGIE.
WHY DO YOU BELIEVE
THAT GEORGE LEFT YOU
THAT FROG?
BECAUSE SHE KNEW
I NEEDED IT.
NO, HONEY, WHAT I MEAN IS...
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK YOU NEED TO GO
WITH YOUR FATHER AND I
TO THE PET PARLOR.
YEAH, YOU KNOW?
YOU COULD GET OUT OF SCHOOL
A LITTLE EARLY.
WOULD YOU LIKE THAT?NO.
KEEP THE FROG
OUT OF THE BATHTUB.
WHAT CAN I GET YOU?THE USUAL.
ICED TEA WITHOUT THE ICE?
THAT'S IT.
TO GO, PLEASE.
THANK YOU.
YOU STILL DOING
THAT "NO ICE" NONSENSE?
HEY, YOU GO DOWN
WITH THE TITANIC,
SEE HOW YOU FEEL ABOUT ICE.
FAIR ENOUGH.
FOR THE RECORD...
I'M NOT DOING THIS,
BUT SEEING
AS WE GO BACK A WAYS...
IS THIS YOUR REAP?
I DON'T KNOW
IF I'M DOING YOU A FAVOR.
I DON'T EITHER.
THANKS, KIFFANY.
DON'T BE A STRANGER.
OKAY.
WELL, LOOK WHO'S HERE.
OH, MY GOD, ROXY.
I HEARD YOU WERE A COP.
FROM WHO?OH, YOU KNOW,
THE OLD GRAPEVINE.
YOU LOOK GREAT.
I LOOK LIKE I ALWAYS LOOK.
TO WHAT DO WE
OWE THIS HONOR?
HIS DAUGHTER'S
GOING TO DIE TODAY.
TAKE CARE OF THE OLD FOOL.
I'M SORRY.
I TRIED TO TALK
DAISY INTO IT.
GEORGIE, PLEASE.
COME ON.
I WOULD MAKE
A REALLY BLOODY GREAT
ROOMMATE, YOU KNOW?
I MAKE
THESE BOYSENBERRY COBBLERS
THAT WOULD BRING TEARS
TO YOUR EYES.
ACTUALLY, YOUR BREATH IS
BRINGING TEARS TO MY EYES.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I COULD BE THE WATCHDOG,
YOU KNOW, SECURITY.
[BARKS]
SERIOUSLY, MASON,
YOU NEED TO GET CLOSE
TO A TOOTHBRUSH.
OH, GOD.
I'LL LIVE OFF THE WILD,
YOU KNOW?
I'VE GOT CUNNING.
I'VE GOT STREET SMARTS.
WAIT, YOU LIVED
TO WHAT, 27?
I KNOW, BUT ALL I KNOW IS
I'M BORN FOR JUNGLE LIFE.
[SINGING]
♪ GIVE IT TO ME
I COULD DO THIS.
LAST TIME I CHECKED,
YOU DIDN'T EXACTLY HAVE
THE GREATEST SUCCESS
IN STREET SALES.
COME ON, LOOK.
HE'S DOING REALLY WELL.
I COULD DO THIS.
THAT'S BECAUSE HE'S CUTE,
AND HE CAN SING.
I'M CUTE.
[♪♪]
GEORGE.
THAT DOLLAR COULD BE PART
OF THE "FREE MASON" FUND.
"FREE MASON."
GOOD ONE.I DON'T GET IT.
YOU'RE REALLY GOOD.
THANKS.
YOU WORK
AROUND HERE?
SORT OF.
I WORK
DIFFERENT PLACES,
EVERYWHERE, REALLY.
UM...
SO I GUESS
YOU WORK HERE.
JUST MOVED HERE
FROM NEW YORK.
I WAS PLAYING
ALL OVER MANHATTAN.
THAT'S IMPRESSIVE.
NO, WELL,
I WAS...
PLAYING
IN THE SUBWAY SYSTEM.
IT FEELS GOOD
TO BE OUTSIDE AGAIN.
I WAS UNDERGROUND
FOR A YEAR.
I JUST FEEL SO ALIVE AGAIN.
ENJOY THAT WHILE YOU CAN.
OKAY.
OKAY, REALLY NICE
TO MEET YOU,
MY ROCK BROTHER,
YOU KNOW?
KEEP ON KEEPING ON,
AND LIVE FAST, DIE YOUNG.
YOU KNOW, LEAVE
A GOOD-LOOKING CORPSE,
AND HERE'S A QUARTER.
I LOVE YOUR VOICE. BYE.
UH, BYE.
MASON, I WAS GETTING
SOME PIANO-MAN ATTENTION.
OKAY, BUT DON'T
KILL THAT MOMENT
BY PROLONGING IT,
BY GEORGE,
AND I STOLE HIS MONEY.
MASON, HE KNOWS
YOU STOLE HIS MONEY.
ONE MISSISSIPPI.
TWO MISSISSIPPI.
REAPERS ARE SUPPOSED TO HIDE.
I MEAN, SURE,
YOU MIGHT BUMP INTO US
ON THE STREET,
BUT THAT'S NOBODY.
THREE MISSISSIPPI, FOUR...
WE STAY IN THE SHADOWS
WHERE NO ONE
WILL EVER FIND US.
GEORGIA LASS.
WHAT?
WHAT?I MEAN, WHO?
GEORGIA LASS.
I DON'T KNOW
WHO THAT IS.
YOU MUST HAVE
HEARD ABOUT HER.
POOR THING.
A PIECE
OF THE SOVIET SPACE STATION
FELL RIGHT OUT OF THE
SKY AND... PFFT.
RIGHT. I DO REMEMBER.
GEORGIA LASS.
ALL RIGHT, I GOT IT.
I HIRED HER
LAST YEAR,
AND LET ME
TELL YOU SOMETHING.
THIS GEORGIA LASS...
WAS THE MOST FASCINATING
WOMAN YOU'D EVER MET?
SHE DISTURBED ME,
AND I CAN'T
QUITE SHAKE HER.
THIS IS FOR
THE PERSONNEL FILES.
I WANT YOU
TO BRING ME HER FILE,
AND MILLIE...
WHAT?
THE PERSONNEL FILES
ARE FOR EXECUTIVES ONLY.
REMEMBER, GEORGIA--
JESUS, I HEARD YOU
THE FIRST THREE TIMES.
HEY, REGGIE, HOW YOU DOING?
FINE.
CAN I GET YOU ANYTHING?
NO.
YOUR DAD'S HERE.
GO AWAY.
USUALLY, YOU CAN'T COMPETE
WITH THE DEAD.
NO ONE SPEAKS ILL
OF THE DEAD.
DEAD PEOPLE ARE ALWAYS NICER,
PRETTIER, SMARTER...
DEATH HAS A WAY
OF CLEANING UP
A GIRL'S REPUTATION.
SO, WHAT THE FUCK
DID GEORGIA LASS
EVER DO TO DELORES?
ACTUALLY,
THE BETTER QUESTION WAS
WHAT THE FUCK
DID GEORGIA LASS EVER DO?
IS SHE COMING DOWN?
SHE'S STARING AT
HER NEW FROG.
OKAY.
LISTEN, CLANCY...
REGGIE--
OH, NEVER MIND.
NO, JOY. NO NEVER MIND.
NO, IT'S REALLY NOTHING.
JOY, HOW CAN I PARENT HER
IF I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE HELL
I'M DEALING WITH HERE?
REGGIE THINKS
J.D. ISN'T DEAD.
THAT'S COMPLETELY NORMAL.
SHE THINKS
GEORGE LEFT HER THE FROG.
THAT'S NOT.
I THINK IT'S TIME
SHE WENT BACK
INTO COUNSELING.
[KNOCKING]HI, JOY. GOT A MINUTE?
OH, ACTUALLY, CLAIRE,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I REALLY DON'T RIGHT NOW.
OH, HI, CLANCY.
CLAIRE.
OKAY. I JUST WANTED
TO TELL YOU
THAT THREE
OF MY BEST FRIENDS
SAW HOW YOU ORGANIZED
MY KITCHEN,
AND EVERY SINGLE ONE OF THEM
WANTS TO CALL YOU.
OH, THAT'S--
THAT'S GREAT...
BUT MAYBE WE COULD TALK
ABOUT THIS TOMORROW, OKAY,
BECAUSE NOW
IS JUST NOT SO GREAT A TIME.
AND I ALSO WANTED TO ASK YOU
IF YOU WOULD TAKE A LOOK
AT MY PRESENT-WRAPPING
STATION.
I THINK I COULD SET IT UP
A LITTLE BETTER
IN THE FAMILY ROOM--
WHAT ABOUT
"NOW'S NOT A GOOD TIME"
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
CLANCY.EXCUSE ME?
YOU LEFT THE GATE
TO OUR YARD OPEN?
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
THE HELL YOU DON'T.
CLANCY.NO, JOY, LET'S SAY IT.
THIS IS THE WOMAN
WHO COMPLAINS ABOUT OUR DOG
TAKING A CRAP
INTO HER PRECIOUS FLOWERS
AND THEN, SUDDENLY,
THE DOG
IS ACCIDENTALLY LET OUT
AND THEN DIES.
HE'S JUST UPSET.
HE LOVED THE DOG.
I'M SORRY FOR YOUR LOSS...
AGAIN.
I'M GOING TO GO NOW.
YOU DO THAT.
TRY NOT TO KILL
ANY MORE DOGS.
JESUS CHRIST, CLANCY,
I STILL LIVE HERE.
I HAVE TO SEE HER.
THINGS HAVE TO BE SAID.
SO. COUNSELING FOR REGGIE.
OR WHOEVER'S INTERESTED
AND AVAILABLE.
I JUST FEEL SICK,
SICK AND TIRED...
AND I MISS THE STUPID DOG.
I MISS YOU.
I MISS MY DAUGHTERS.
I MISS EVERYTHING.
WHO THE FUCK
YOU CALLING INSOLENT?
WHEN INTERVIEWING,
THEY TELL YOU TO RELAX,
TO JUST BE YOURSELF.
WELL, LOOK WHAT THAT GOT ME.
I'M ALREADY DEAD.
CURIOSITY CAN'T KILL ME.
I BET THEY ALL LIED
TO DELORES.
WHAT ARE THEY ALL HIDING?
WHAT'S THE REAL STORY?
SO, MISTY?
ANY CHILDREN?
NO.
ARE YOU SINGLE?
YES.
MISTY.
I HAVE TWO CHILDREN,
SASSOON AND JORDACHE,
AND...
I THINK I'M STILL MARRIED
IN THE STATE OF LOUISIANA
AND PROBABLY KANSAS.
TOPEKA'S IN KANSAS,
ISN'T IT?
SPECIAL FORCES, CRYSTAL?
GOD, I COULDN'T EVEN
LAND THIS JOB
WITHOUT A NOTE FROM MY MOM.
I GUESS EVERYBODY
OWES SOMEBODY ELSE
SOMETHING,
SOMETHING THEY HAVE TO DO.
HI, ROSIE.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING UP?
YOU SHOULD
BE ASLEEP, PEANUT.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
GO BACK TO SLEEP.
BUT I'M UP NOW.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING, PAPA?
I'M GOING TO GET A FEW THINGS
YOUR MOTHER NEEDS.
WHEN ARE YOU COMING BACK?
SOON.
♪ I'LL BE LOVING YOU
SING IT, PAPA.
ALWAYS ♪
♪ WITH A LOVE THAT'S TRUE
♪ WHEN THINGS YOU'VE PLANNED
NEED A HELPING HAND ♪
♪ I WILL UNDERSTAND
ALWAYS ♪
HELL, NO,
YOU CAN'T LIVE WITH ME.
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE YOU CAN'T.
WHY? WHY, WHY, WHY,
WHY, WHY, WHY, WHY?
BECAUSE I LIVE THERE,
AND YOU DRIVE ME
FUCKING NUTS AS IT IS.
OKAY. I'M HOMELESS
AND PROUD OF IT.
WELL, YOU SHOULD BE.
ALL THESE FUCKING ASSUMPTIONS
SOCIETY MAKES, MAN.
IT'S, LIKE, YOU KNOW,
GET A JOB, EAT FOOD,
LIVE IN A HOUSE.
IT'S FASCISM, THAT IS,
ABSOLUTE FUCKING FASCISM.
I WON'T TAKE IT.
I'M GOING TO LIVE
IN THE MOMENT.
I'M LIVING OFF THE LAND.
SOUNDS LIKE LOITERING.
PLEASE, LET ME
LIVE WITH YOU, ROXY.
PLEASE, I'LL SLEEP
IN THE BLOODY BATHTUB.
THEN WHAT WILL I TELL
MY BOYFRIEND?
WHAT?SEE? YOU DON'T KNOW ME.
OKAY.
LIVE OFF THE LAND.
FUCKING PIONEER.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO
STAKE MY OWN CLAIM
AND CLAIM MY OWN STEAK.
I MEAN, IT'S JUST LIKE
PICKING BERRIES,
REALLY, ISN'T IT?
UGH.
FORAGING IN NATURE.
DID YOU TAKE THAT MAN'S STEAK?
HE WAS FINISHED,
AND WE WOULDN'T WANT
TO WASTE FOOD, NOW,
WOULD WE, KIFFANY,
NOT WHEN THERE ARE CHILDREN
STARVING IN BOSTON.
HOW ABOUT MY PAYING CUSTOMER?
I'LL HAVE A COBB SALAD,
KIFFANY.
YOU'RE MAKING
ALL THE WRONG MOVES, MASON.
RIGHT.
COFFEE?
NO, THANK YOU.
I KNOW YOU DIDN'T
JUST STEAL THAT MONEY
FROM ME.
I WAS KEEPING IT
SAFE FOR YOU.
I WANTED YOU
TO GET-GET IT.
YOU'RE OUT.
OUT?THAT'S RIGHT.
OUT OF MY HOUSE.
THIS IS DER WAFFLE HAUS.
AND YOU'RE DER-OUT-OF-HERE.
KIFFANY, I'VE HAD
A REALLY BAD...
COUPLE OF DAYS.
THAT'S ONE COBB SALAD,
AND HE BETTER BE GONE
BY THE TIME I GET BACK.
YOU HEARD
WHAT THE LADY SAID.
YOU GOT TO GO.
NO.
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD
OF POLICE BRUTALITY?
BECAUSE THAT
IS POLICE BRUTALITY.
YOU REALLY DON'T GET IT,
DO YOU, MASON?
THIS IS OUR HOME,
AND YOU JUST PISSED
ALL OVER IT.
I WAS LIVING OFF
THE FAT OF THE LAND.
NO, WHAT YOU WERE DOING
WAS DISRESPECTING
THE LAST PLACE
YOU ACTUALLY BELONG
AND THE ONLY
LIVING PERSON YOU KNOW
THAT PUTS UP
WITH YOUR
FREEZE-DRIED BULLSHIT.
DO YOU CALL THAT
PUTTING UP WITH ME?
I'D CALL THAT
BREAKING THE CAMEL'S BACK.
ENJOY THE STREETS,
MASON,
THAT'S ALL YOU GOT.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
YEAH. ME TOO.
I FEEL LIKE I'VE
BEEN HERE BEFORE.
YOU'VE BURIED
AN ANIMAL HERE BEFORE?
NO, BUT...
I'M HAVING THE MOST
POWERFUL SENSE OF DEJA VU.
IT'S WEIRD.
GOOD AFTERNOON.
I'M JED.
CAN I OFFER YOU FOLKS
A COLD BEVERAGE OR A SNACK?
NO, THANK YOU.
I'M GOOD. REG?
NO, THANKS.
YOU'VE LOOKED OVER THE OPTIONS
FOR BURIAL AND CREMATION?
ARE THERE ANY QUESTIONS?
I FEEL LIKE
I'VE BEEN HERE BEFORE.
IS THAT CRAZY?
YOU PROBABLY
REMEMBER IT IN ITS
PREVIOUS INCARNATION...
AS A FOSTER'S FREEZE.
I WAS ON THE GRILL,
AND MY WIFE WAS
ON THE TILL.
IS SHE A REDHEAD?
MORE AUBURN, REALLY.
NO REAL FUTURE
IN MILKSHAKES,
I'M AFRAID.
DEATH JUST MAKES
MUCH BETTER BUSINESS SENSE.
WELL...
CONGRATULATIONS.
THANK YOU.
THAT'S FOR YOUR
SMALLER DOG,
YOUR YORKIE,
YOUR LHASA APSO,
YOUR SHIH TZU,
YOUR CHIHUAHUA,
AND YOUR WIENER DOG,
ANYTHING IN
YOUR TOY GROUP.
J.D. WAS A BIG DOG.
HE WAS A GOLDEN RETRIEVER.
WELL, I'M SURE HE WAS
A VERY BEAUTIFUL DOG.
HE REALLY WAS.
UH, I THINK WE MIGHT NEED
SOME MORE TIME
TO DISCUSS THIS
AS A FAMILY.
ABSOLUTELY.
YOU AND YOUR HUSBAND
AND YOUR DAUGHTER,
YOU TAKE ALL THE TIME
YOU WANT, OKAY?
ACTUALLY, WE'RE...MM-HMM.
YEAH.
OKAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHY DON'T WE
TAKE J.D. HOME
AND DO THIS TOGETHER?
WOULD THAT BE OKAY, REG?
OKAY.
[GEORGE]:
THE THINGS WE DO FOR LOVE.
RAY.
[SNARLING]
GO AWAY.
DEAD GIRL, COMING THROUGH.
OH, MILLIE,
THAT'S TERRIBLE.
JUST STATING THE FACTS.
WELL, LET'S SEE
WHAT WE HAVE HERE.
NOT MUCH.
I-- NOT THAT I WAS
LOOKING AT IT.
IT'S JUST KIND OF,
YOU KNOW... THIN.
WELL, YOU'RE
IN THE KNOW NOW.
MIGHT AS WELL
HEAR THIS WITH ME.
"ATTITUDE-- INSOLENT."
DON'T YOU THINK
THE BETTER WORD WOULD BE...
SAUCY?
AM I RIGHT
OR AM I RIGHT?
SHE WAS SAUCY.
"WITHOUT MANNERS.
NO RESPECT FOR AUTHORITY."
[CLICKS TONGUE]
KIDS TODAY, I TELL YOU.
"AMBITION-- NONE."
MAYBE SHE JUST DIDN'T SHARE
HER AMBITION WITH YOU.
WELL, I CERTAINLY
DIDN'T SEE ANY.
"FUTURE FORECAST--
WON'T LAST LONG."
WELL, YOU NAILED THAT ONE.
HER POOR MOTHER.
YEAH.
AT LEAST SHE WAS PRETTY.
WHAT'S SHE
GOING TO THINK
WHEN SHE READS THIS?
WHY WOULD SHE DO THAT?
SHE CAME TO SEE ME.
I TOLD HER I'D GIVE HER
MY PAPERWORK
ON HER DAUGHTER.
I FELT IT WAS THE LEAST
I COULD DO.
SUCH A SHORT LIFE.
ANYTHING SHE
MIGHT HAVE TOUCHED,
IT'S PRECIOUS.
YOU CAN'T SHOW THAT
TO HER MOTHER.
MILLIE.
I TRASH-TALKED A DEAD GIRL
ON THIS PAGE,
AND NOW I TO HAVE TO
LIVE WITH THAT.
WELL, IT'S NOT TOO LATE--
OH, MILLIE, IT IS.
NO, IT'S NOT!
[WHISPERING]:
A LITTLE WHITE-OUT AND
NO ONE'S THE WISER.
ARE YOU SUGGESTING
WE TAMPER
WITH OFFICIAL
HAPPY TIME DOCUMENTS?
I'M NOT SAYING...
I'M JUST SAYING...
THAT'S AGAINST EVERYTHING
I STAND FOR.
NOT EVERYTHING.
NOT EVERYTHING YOU TAUGHT ME.
IT'S JUST...
IT'S THE RIGHT THING TO DO.
DO YOU WANT TO TYPE
OR SHOULD I?
I KNOW WHAT TO DO.
I STILL THINK
WE SHOULD SAY
SHE WAS
A MISUNDERSTOOD GENIUS.
I THINK SHE WAS
COMPLICATED, MILLIE.
SHE WASN'T A GENIUS.
BUT SHE SEEMED SMART, RIGHT?
VERY. AND FUNNY.
AN ODD CHARM,
A CERTAIN  JE NE SAIS QUOI...
I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT TO WRITE.
I KNOW WHAT WILL MAKE
HER MOTHER PROUD.
WHAT?
I'M GOING TO
BASE HER ON YOU.
I THOUGHT WE WANTED TO
MAKE HER SEEM...
IMPRESSIVE.
YOU ARE IMPRESSIVE.
I'VE WATCHED YOU.
IN ONE YEAR, MILLIE,
IN ONE SHORT YEAR,
YOU'VE GROWN
INTO A FINE YOUNG WOMAN.
I'M SURE GEORGIA'S MOM
WILL BE PLEASED.
MAYBE THERE ARE
NO SECOND CHANCES IN LIFE...
DONE.
BUT THEN AGAIN,
WHAT DO I KNOW?
[PLAYING SYNTHESIZER]
IT'S A HARD WAY
TO EARN A LIVING.
ANY DAY ABOVE GROUND
IS A GOOD ONE, RIGHT?
YEAH, ENJOY THAT
WHILE YOU CAN.
RAY.
YOU KNOW,
I'M KIND OF A GYM RAT.
YEAH.
YEAH, SPIN CLASS, YOGA...
A LITTLE TAE BO.
LOOK, BABY,
I DON'T WANT TO BRAG,
BUT I'M HUNG LIKE A JURY.
MY NAME'S PETE.
DOLLAR FOR A TUNE?
DOESN'T IT BOTHER YOU,
HAVING TO DEPEND ON
OTHER PEOPLE'S HANDOUTS?
I'VE ALWAYS RELIED
ON THE KINDNESS
OF STRANGERS.
WELL, I'VE PLAYED
BLANCHE DUBOIS
FOR A LIFETIME, SO...
SO YOU MUST GET IT.
I DO.
WHAT WAS THAT?
IT'S FOR LUCK.
IF YOU'VE GOT A GOOD ONE,
NOW WOULD BE THE TIME.
NO, I CAN
GO ALL NIGHT.
I'M LIKE AN ANIMAL, BABY.
YEAH, I'M DANGEROUS.
I'M LIKE A BULL MOOSE
IN HEAT. MM!
CREDIT CARD?
WHAT, YOU NEED
MY CREDIT CARD ALREADY?
I MEAN,
WE HARDLY KNOW EACH OTHER.
ALL WE'RE DOING
IS TALKING HERE, RIGHT?
I MEAN, FOR GOD'S SAKE,
I'VE STILL GOT MY PANTS ON.
HOLY SHIT.
FUCK ME.
NO, NO, NOT YOU, SWEETHEART.
♪ STARING AT A MAPLE LEAF
♪ LEANING ON THE MOTHER TREE
♪ I SAID TO MYSELF--
[PEOPLE SHOUTING]
[WOMAN]: CALL AN AMBULANCE!
WHAT HAPPENED?
DID YOU KILL ME?
NO. I'M YOUR REAPER.
YOU DIED AND...
UH-OH.
AM I DEAD?
GO AWAY.
[GROWLS]
I HAVEN'T FIGURED OUT
WHO SHE IS YET.
I'LL LET YOU KNOW.
SHE'S OVER THERE.
THAT'S ROSIE.
I DON'T THINK
I CAN DO THIS.
[GEORGE]:
WE THINK WE CAN'T
DO SOMETHING.
WE THINK WE CAN'T,
WE THINK WE CAN'T...
BUT WE CAN.
[RIBBITS]
[EXHALES]
OKAY, BOY.
SWEETIE, DO YOU
WANT TO SAY SOMETHING?
I'M SURE J.D.
WOULD LIKE IT IF YOU DID.
DEAR J.D.--IT'S NOT A LETTER,
SWEETHEART.
CLANCY.SORRY.
DEAR J.D...
IF YOU SEE GEORGE,
TELL HER I SAY, "HEY."
TELL HER IT'S ALL RIGHT
TO COME BACK...
AND TELL HER
THANKS FOR THE FROG.
OKAY, WELL,
THAT WAS LOVELY, SWEETHEART.
I'M NOT DONE.
GOOD.
I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY I
LEFT THE GATE OPEN.
I'M SORRY I GOT YOU KILLED.
LEAVING THE GATE OPEN
DIDN'T KILL J.D., SWEETHEART.
THERE'S LOTS OF DOGS
WHO RUN ALL OVER THE PLACE,
AND THEY'RE OKAY.
J.D. DIED...
BECAUSE IT WAS JUST TIME
FOR THAT TO HAPPEN.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT,
SWEETHEART.
NONE OF IT IS.
[KNOCKING]
I DIDN'T SAY
YOU COULD SIT DOWN.
THESE ARE FOR YOU.
DID YOU STEAL THOSE?
NO.
I PICKED THEM.
FROM WHERE?
THE FOREST.
POSIES DON'T GROW
IN THE SHADE.
OKAY, I PICKED THEM
FROM SOMEBODY'S YARD,
BUT THERE WERE
LITERALLY THOUSANDS--
ACTUALLY, MILLIONS OF THEM,
SO I DON'T THINK
THEY'LL BE MISSED,
AND THE POINT IS,
I PICKED THEM FOR YOU,
SO THAT'S GOT TO
SAY SOMETHING?
IF YOU STOLE THEM,
I DON'T WANT THEM.
I'M SORRY.
KIFFANY...
THAT WAS TERRIBLE OF ME.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE STOLEN
YOUR TIP.
IT WASN'T MY TABLE.
IT WAS KIRSTIN'S.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
IF IT WASN'T YOUR TIP,
WHY ARE YOU SO MAD AT ME?
WE POOL OUR TIPS.
IF SOMEONE HAS
A GOOD MORNING,
EVERYONE HAS
A GOOD MORNING.
IF SOMEONE GETS STIFFED,
EVERYBODY
GETS STIFFED.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND
WHAT THAT MEANS?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU DON'T WANT
YOUR POSIES.
I DON'T THINK YOU UNDERSTAND
THE MEANING
OF THE WORD "HOUSE."
IT'S A PLACE
WHERE I CAN SLEEP.
A PLACE
WHERE YOU CAN FEEL SAFE.
I DON'T FEEL SAFE ANYWHERE.
I'VE BEEN HAVING
A FUCK OF A TIME LATELY,
KIFFANY...
JUST A WORLD OF PAIN...
SAME OLD, SAME OLD, EH?
SIT.
[SIGHS]
I WORK HARD.
I TAKE ORDERS.
I BRING PEOPLE
THEIR FOOD.
IT'S VERY SIMPLE.
NO MYSTERY.
YOU KNOW
WHY I STAY HERE?
BECAUSE YOU LOVE WAFFLES?
IT'S A CLEAN,
WELL-LIGHTED PLACE...
AND I FEEL SAFE.
HERE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
SAY, "THANK YOU."
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
HEY.
YOU CAN'T SLEEP HERE.
SO...
I GUESS I HAVE TO
APOLOGIZE TO CLAIRE.
THAT'D BE NICE.
OR YOU COULD
APOLOGIZE FOR ME.
NO.
WHAT A FUCKING DAY.
YEAH.SO, WHAT'S FOR DINNER?
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT YOU SHOULD PROBABLY GO.
I JUST THOUGHT...
I MEAN,
IF REGGIE NEEDS ANYTHING.
YEAH, THANKS...
BUT YOU SHOULD
PROBABLY GO HOME.
YOU WERE
A GOOD FATHER TODAY.
THANKS.
DOESN'T MAKE YOU
A GOOD HUSBAND.
I KNOW.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO GO
FOR A WALK?
NO.
ARE YOU HUNGRY?
I THINK THEY'RE
SERVING DINNER.
NO.
I'M WAITING
FOR SOMEONE.
HI, ROSIE.
HI, PAPA.
I'M SORRY.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
SHH.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
GO TO SLEEP.
♪ I'LL BE LOVING YOU
SING IT, PAPA.
ALWAYS ♪
♪ WITH A LOVE THAT'S TRUE
♪ AND THE THINGS
YOU'VE PLANNED ♪
♪ NEED A HELPING HAND
♪ I WILL UNDERSTAND
ALWAYS, ALWAYS ♪
♪ DAYS MAY NOT BE FAIR
ALWAYS ♪
♪ THAT'S WHEN I'LL BE THERE
♪ NOT FOR JUST AN HOUR
♪ NOT FOR JUST A DAY
♪ NOT FOR JUST A YEAR
♪ BUT ALWAYS
ARE YOU LEAVING AGAIN, PAPA?
NO, ROSIE.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
HE'S NOT STAYING HERE.
YOU'RE BEING TOTALLY SELFISH.
THAT'S A FINE SENTIMENT
COMING FROM YOU.
EXCUSE ME?
I AM THE MOST--
SELF-INVOLVED IS WHAT
YOU ARE, GEORGIA.
YOU ARE ALWAYS
IN YOUR OWN HEAD.
IT'S LIKE YOU'RE TALKING
TO YOURSELF.
AM I?
SHE HAS GOT
A POINT, GEORGIE.
[BOTH]: SHUT UP, MASON.
FINE. JESUS.
HE CAN HAVE DINNER WITH US.
BUT THEN HE HAS TO GO.
HE CAN'T STAY.
SO, WHAT?
IS HE A DOG NOW?
SHOULD WE JUST PUT HIS
FOOD IN A BOWL
AND LEAVE IT OUT BACK?
I ACTUALLY
WOULDN'T MIND THAT.
SHUT THE FUCK UP, MASON.
I AM TRYING
TO PROTECT HIM.
HOW IS KICKING SOMEONE
TO THE CURB
GOING TO PROTECT THEM?
YOU JUST THINK
EVERYONE IS IN LOVE
WITH YOU.
WELL, MAYBE THEY AREN'T.
MAYBE THEY JUST NEED
A PLACE TO FEEL SAFE.
THAT WAS VERY MEAN, GEORGIA.
BUT NOT ENTIRELY INACCURATE.
ENOUGH, MASON.
[RAY HISSING]
NO ONE IS SAFE HERE.
THIS IS WHERE YOU KILLED HIM.
HE'S NOT COMING BACK.
HE DID.
TODAY.
THERE WAS SUPPOSED TO
BE ONE DEATH,
AND THERE WERE TWO,
AND IF MASON STAYS HERE,
HE'S JUST GOING TO GET
ANGRIER AND ANGRIER.
DON'T YOU GET IT?
WELL...
IT'S MY HOUSE TOO...
AND I'M NOT SCARED
OF ANYTHING.
FINE.
[WHISPERS]:
THANKS, GEORGIE.
NO PROBLEM-O.
STAY OUT OF MY BEDROOM...
THAT'S NO FUN,
MY DARLING.
AND IF YOU'RE
NOT SCARED,
YOU'RE JUST A FOOL.
[SIGHS] OH, GOODNESS,
GRACIOUS ME.
[GROANS]
GHOST STORIES?
PAINT EACH OTHER'S
TOENAILS?
JUST GO TO SLEEP, MASON.
YOU'LL STAY HERE
FOR A LITTLE BIT, WILL YOU?
SURE.
PULL THE COVERS
OVER YOUR HEAD.
NO WAY.
IT ALWAYS MADE ME MORE SCARED,
BEING IN THE DARK.
WILL YOU LEAVE
THE LIGHT ON?
I'LL JUST STAY HERE
UNTIL YOU FALL ASLEEP.
I DON'T THINK
I'LL EVER FALL ASLEEP AGAIN.
[SNORING]
[GEORGE]:
ONE MISSISSIPPI.
TWO MISSISSIPPI.
MASON.
I GUESS THERE'S
ALWAYS SOMETHING OUT THERE
TO HIDE FROM,
SOMETHING OUT THERE
YOU JUST CAN'T FACE.
THREE MISSISSIPPI.
FOUR MISSISSIPPI.
SO YOU'LL HIDE
FOR AS LONG AS YOU CAN...
BUT THAT'S NOT EASY EITHER,
ALL THAT HIDING...
[RAY GROWLS]
FIVE MISSISSIPPI.
IN THE END,
WHAT YOU WERE SO AFRAID OF
TURNS OUT NOT TO BE
SO SCARY AFTER ALL.
SIX MISSISSIPPI, SEVEN.
BECAUSE YOU HAVE TO KNOW
THAT IF YOU'RE HIDING,
MORE OFTEN THAN NOT,
YOUR FEARS
WILL COME LOOKING FOR YOU.
COME OUT, COME OUT,
WHEREVER YOU ARE.
[SNARLS]
I NEVER LIKED YOU, RAY.
[SHRIEKING]
OLLY, OLLY, OXEN FREE.