[GEORGE]:  I'VE NEVER
BELONGED TO A CLUB.
I MEAN, I GET THEM,
I JUST DON'T WANT
TO BE IN THEM.
LIKE BOOK CLUBS.
"HEY,
CHECK OUT HOW SMART WE ARE.
WE CAN READ."
SHUT UP, ALREADY.
AND BICYCLE CLUBS.
WHAT'S THAT ABOUT?
ONE GUY IN A BAD OUTFIT,
YOU'RE A TOOL.
FOUR GUYS
IN THE SAME GOOFY SHIRT,
SUDDENLY, YOU'RE THE SHIT?
GIVE ME A BREAK.
MY PARENTS ALWAYS TOLD ME
TO JOIN SOME CLUB AT SCHOOL,
ANY CLUB AT ALL,
JUST PICK A CARD,
BUT I DIDN'T,
AND THEN A CLUB
FINALLY PICKED ME.
I DON'T THINK THIS IS
WHAT MY PARENTS HAD IN MIND.
DID YOU ROB A GRAVE
OR SOMETHING?NO.
I WAS COMBING THROUGH
SOMEBODY'S GARBAGE
LOOKING FOR THEIR
CREDIT CARD RECEIPTS.
THAT'S TERIYAKI SAUCE.
HERE, SMELL.NOT WHILE I'M EATING.
WELL, YOUR FINGERNAILS
COULD USE A LITTLE SPA TIME.
AW, THANKS.
NOT WHILE I'M EATING.
OH, BLOODY HELL.
SORRY, I DIDN'T THINK
YOU WOULD DO THAT
AT THE TABLE.
I CAN'T WIN
WITH YOU PEOPLE,
CAN'T I?
YOU'RE MOANING ABOUT
MY PERSONAL HYGIENE.
YOU'RE GOING ON
ABOUT MY ETIQUETTE.
I CAN'T FUCKING WIN.
MASON, IF YOU WEREN'T
A REAPER, WHERE WOULD
YOU BE RIGHT NOW?
DEAD.BUT IF YOU WEREN'T DEAD.
I'D BE DEAD.
I'D BE BACK IN COLLEGE,
A SOPHOMORE.
IT'S ENOUGH TO MAKE YOU
GLAD YOU'RE DEAD.
[CRYING]
IT'S TOO EARLY
FOR THIS CRAP.
WE'RE MOVING.
WE'VE ORDERED.
THEY'LL FIGURE OUT.
THEY'RE
REALLY SMART HERE.
LET'S GO.
WHAT CAN I GET FOR YOU?
NOTHING, KIFFANY, THANK YOU.
YOU'RE NOT ORDERING
BREAKFAST TODAY?
NO, I'VE HAD BREAKFAST.
WHERE DID YOU EAT?
HUNGRY PETE'S,
JUST DOWN THE STREET.
ESCAPE FROM ROUTINE,
IT IS GOOD FOR THE SOUL.
HOW WAS IT?
AWFUL.
NEVER GOING BACK.
A TICKET TO CANCUN,
FIRST CLASS?
ARE YOU SHITTING ME?
THERE'S A POST-IT ON IT,
DUMB ASS.
IF YOU ARE PUTTING ME
ON A PLANE THAT'S GOING DOWN,
I SWEAR TO GOD--
I CAN'T SWIM, RUBE.
THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
THERE'S ONE
POST-IT EACH.
ODDS ARE THERE ARE
MORE THAN TWO PEOPLE
ON THAT PLANE.
ODDS ARE IF
THE PLANE GOES DOWN,
EVERYONE'S GOING TO DIE.
ODDS ARE THAT PLANE
AIN'T GOING DOWN.
PRESIDENT OF THE MATH CLUB?
JUST SMARTER
THAN MASON.
REALLY?
WELL, LOOK AT YOU...
WHAT'S
THE MONTGOMERY CLUB?
OLD-LINE COUNTRY CLUB,
BEAUTIFUL GOLF COURSE,
OLD MONEY, BIG MONEY.
MONEY MONEY.
DON'T GET LOST ON THE GREEN.
SHE GETS A VIP REAP
LAST WEEK,
AND THIS WEEK...
MONTGOMERY CLUB?
IT'S JUST NOT FAIR.
WELL, THAT'S NOT MY CALL.
HUMOR ME?
GIVE YOURSELF
EXTRA TIME.
SEE HOW THAT OTHER HALF LIVES.
ISN'T THAT WHAT
I'VE BEEN DOING?
NOTHING FOR ME TODAY?NO, NOTHING FOR YOU TODAY.
WHAT'S YOURS?
ME, I'VE GOT A
1019 WEST SLANE STREET
OUTSIDE ROOM 216.
SOUNDS LIKE A HOTEL.
MAYBE A MURDER.
MAYBE.
I'M KIND OF IN THE MOOD
FOR A MURDER.
HMM.
WHAT IS THIS?
THAT, MY DEAR,
IS THE VERY SAME ORGANIC
WHOLE GRAIN BANANA NUT BREAD
THAT WON ME A BLUE RIBBON
AT THE NEW MEXICO
STATE FAIR IN 1975.
WHY WERE YOU
IN NEW MEXICO?
I WAS MANAGING A LLAMA RANCH
OUTSIDE OF SANTA FE.
IT SMELLS BAD.
ARE YOU ALWAYS SO AFRAID
OF TRYING SOMETHING NEW?
IF I THINK IT CAME OUT OF
A LLAMA'S BUTT.
FINE.
BE A CONFORMIST.
HAVE CAP'N CRUNCH.
MOM NEVER TOLD ME
SHE LIVED ON A LLAMA RANCH.
THAT'S BECAUSE
MOM NEVER DID.
YOUR MOM WAS
IN THE SEVENTH GRADE
WHILE HER MOM
WAS 800 MILES AWAY
SPREADING HER WINGS.
SANTA FE
WAS SO BEAUTIFUL.
YOU AND YOUR SISTER
WOULD HAVE LOVED IT.
I WANT TO GO.
HONEY, MY LIFE IS
FILLED WITH STORIES.
STORIES DON'T HAPPEN
TO PEOPLE
WHO JUST STAY INSIDE.
REGGIE, GO GET READY
FOR SCHOOL.
I WANT TO HEAR MORE STORIES.
AFTER SCHOOL.
DID YOU KNOW
THAT YOUR GRANDMOTHER
ONCE DID TIME?
YOU WERE IN JAIL?MOM...
DID YOU STEAL SOMETHING?
I WAS IN JAIL
BECAUSE RICHARD NIXON
WAS A LIAR AND AN ASSHOLE.
ALL RIGHT. REGGIE? NOW.
THAT SO DOES NOT WORK
FOR ME.
WHAT?
I CAN'T LISTEN TO YOU
TELL STORY AFTER STORY
ABOUT YOUR SELFISHNESS
AND THEN CALL IT
A LIFE PHILOSOPHY.
I WAS A CONCERNED
AMERICAN CITIZEN.
I WANTED
THE WHITE HOUSE
TO HEAR MY VOICE.
I WAS 11.
I WANTED A RIDE HOME
FROM SCHOOL.
SO TELL ME, JOY,
DID YOU GET HOME
FROM SCHOOL THAT DAY?
YOU CANNOT, IN FRONT
OF AN IMPRESSIONABLE CHILD,
BRAG ABOUT GOING TO JAIL.
SHE'S 12.
SHE CAN HANDLE IT.
SHE'S 11,
AND THAT'S NOT YOUR CALL.
SO ARE YOU PICKING ME UP
AFTER SCHOOL, GRANDMA?
ABSOLUTELY.
OKAY. BYE.
WE'LL HAVE
AN ADVENTURE,
SOMETHING WEIRD.
COOL.
LITTLE GIRLS LOVE ADVENTURES.
AT LEAST, MOST OF THEM DO.
YOU RUN AWAY
YOUR WHOLE LIFE,
AND THEN YOU PARADE IT
AROUND YOU
LIKE A BADGE OF HONOR.
IT'S JUST BEYOND ME.
I DON'T RUN AWAY.
I RUN TOWARDS.
OH, PRETTY.
WHY DON'T YOU
NEEDLE-POINT THAT ON
A PILLOW FOR ME, HUH?
IT'S NOT MY THING.
NO.
YOU DON'T STICK AROUND
ANYWHERE LONG ENOUGH
TO DO THAT KIND OF PROJECT,
DO YOU?
I INVITED YOU TO ITALY.
YOU SAID NO.
MOTHER, YOU DON'T INVITE
A FOURTH GRADER TO ITALY.
YOU EITHER TAKE THEM
OR YOU DON'T.
RIGHT? I MEAN,
MAKE A FUCKING CHOICE.
I'M NOT THAT GIRL.
NOT WHAT GIRL?
THE GIRL
CLANCY IS SLEEPING WITH.
STOP TAKING IT OUT ON ME.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?AWAY FROM YOU.
[GEORGE]:
I GUESS WHEN YOU WANT
TO RUN AWAY FROM YOUR LIFE,
YOU JUST MAKE A BREAK FOR IT
AND HOPE NO ONE'S LOOKING.
HEY, REGGIE.
IMAGINE YOURSELF
ON THE ISLAND OF KOMODO,
FACE TO FACE
WITH THE TERRIFYING DRAGON
THAT ROAMS ITS SHORES.
THAT'S A KOMODO DRAGON?
YEAH, I'M SHOWING
MY DRAGON TO SEVERAL
CLASSES THIS MORNING.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO
BE MY ASSISTANT?
WHAT DO I HAVE TO DO?
JUST STAND THERE
AND LOOK PRETTY.
CAN I TOUCH IT?
DON'T BE ABSURD.
THE KOMODO DRAGON
IS A DANGEROUS CARNIVORE.
HE'LL EAT YOU
LIKE YOU'RE A PIECE
OF TURKEY BALONEY,
WHICH,
IN CASE YOU'RE ALL CURIOUS,
IS HIS FAVORITE.
WHAT'S HIS NAME?FRODO.
WHO?
LIKE THE HOBBIT.
HAVE YOU BEEN DEAD
FOR THE LAST SIX YEARS?
SEVEN.
I'M NOT GOING TO HURT HIM.
I JUST WANT TO PET HIM.
FRODO HURTING YOU
IS THE MORE LIKELY SCENARIO.
SO, REGGIE,
DO YOU WANT TO BE
MY ASSISTANT?
MRS. BRODY SAID
I COULD PICK ANYBODY.
SURE.YES!
[BELL RINGS]
GOLDILOCKS LIKES YOU.
HIS NAME IS FRANCIS.
PLEASE PUT IT SOMEWHERE SAFE.
THIS DENT HAPPENED
THE LAST TIME I WAS HERE.
[♪♪]
[SLURPING]
MAY I HELP YOU?
I'M LOOKING FOR INFORMATION
ON THE INTRA-COUNTRY CLUB
WOMEN'S GOLF LEAGUE.
WE DON'T HAVE
AN INTRA-COUNTRY CLUB
WOMEN'S GOLF LEAGUE.
WHICH IS WHY I'M HERE,
TO TALK TO SOMEONE
ABOUT GETTING ONE STARTED.
MISS, THIS IS A PRIVATE CLUB.
I WAS TOLD TO ASK FOR A...
T. HESBURGH?
I'M VERY SORRY, MISS.
MEMBERS ONLY.
WELL, HESBURGH
INVITED ME HERE,
AND NOW I'M HERE,
SO IF YOU WANT
TO TURN ME AWAY,
THAT'S ON YOU, DEAR SIR,
BUT HESBURGH WON'T LIKE IT.
HEADS COULD ROLL.
ROLL.SHE CAN SIT WITH ME.
VERY GOOD, SIR.
I... I KNOW
MR. HESBURGH.
HE'S OUT
ON THE BACK NINE.
YOU CAN TAKE A SEAT
IF YOU WANT.
THAT'S VERY NICE OF YOU.
THANK YOU.
[GEORGE]:  CUTE.
A LITTLE COUNTRY CLUBBY,
BUT CUTE.
I'M TRIP.
OF COURSE YOU ARE.
I'M GEORGE.
AS IN GEORGIA?
GEORGE. THAT'S
A CUTE NICKNAME.
IT'S NOT A NICKNAME...
TRIP.
SO...
WHY DO YOU NEED TO SEE
MR. HESBURGH?IT'S...
PERSONAL.
SINCE WE'RE PRETENDING
TO KNOW EACH OTHER,
LET'S PRETEND
TO LIKE EACH OTHER, TOO.
WELL, YOU SEE,
THE TRUTH IS, TRIP,
I'M A PROCESS SERVER.
HE'S BEING SUED.
BUMMER.
I WORK FOR MR. HESBURGH.
OH.
MAYBE YOU'RE
A TROUBLEMAKER TOO.
MAYBE I'D BETTER STEER CLEAR.
OKAY, YOU DO THAT.
[BELL RINGS]
CHILDREN.
THIS ISN'T A HOTEL.
IT'S A SCHOOL.I CAN SEE THAT.
HI, BUDDY.
TELL ME, WHERE'S ROOM 216?
GO FUCK YOURSELF.
KIDS HAVE CHANGED, HUH?
WELL, IT'S A SCHOOL,
SO THERE ARE NUMBERS
ON THE DOORS.
I CAN SEE THAT.
DON'T TALK TO ME
LIKE I'M A THIRD GRADER.
LET'S GO, YOU'RE LATE.
YOU'RE GOING TO GET WHIPPED.
COME ON. LET'S GO.
YOU HAVE FUN, NOW.OH, NO, NO, NO,
YOU'RE COMING WITH ME.
WHY?'CAUSE YOU CAN TALK
TO THIRD GRADERS.
THEY'RE GOING TO TAKE THE
ELECTRIC CHAIR TO YOU.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN TO YOU?
WELL, I ACTUALLY WRITE
FOR HIS NEWSPAPER,
SO I HAVE TO ASK
THE KEY QUESTION.
WHY IS HE BEING SUED?
THE PAPER LIBELLED SOMEONE.
THEY DEFAMED
SOMEONE'S CHARACTER?
THAT'S THE SAME
THING AS LIBEL.
THE PAPER BOY
KEPT THROWING SOMEONE'S
PAPER IN THE BUSHES?
THAT MUST BE IT.
WELL, YOU SURE ARE
A PRETTY PROCESS SERVER.
MAYBE I'M LYING.
MAYBE I'M REALLY HERE
FOR SOME OTHER REASON.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT YOU.
NO, YOU DON'T.
EXCEPT THAT YOU ARE LYING
ABOUT WHY YOU'RE HERE.
RIGHT.
IS YOUR NAME REALLY GEORGE?
YES. YOU'RE TRIP?
YES.
IVY LEAGUE?YALE. YOU?
DROPOUT. SIBLINGS?
SISTER. YOU?SISTER.
YOU LIVE ALONE?NO.
GUY?ACTRESS.
SUCCESSFUL?NO. SO, YOU'RE RICH?
TRUST FUND. YOU HAVE PETS?
FROG.FROG?
FROG.
AMPHIBIAN. INTERESTING.
FAVORITE FOOD?
WAFFLES. FAVORITE PLACE?
RIGHT NOW?
HERE.
REALLY?
YEAH.
YOU LYING?NO.
MONEY OR FAME?MONEY.
MONEY OR IMMORTALITY?
MONEY.
MONEY OR LOVE?
LIAR.
DO YOU HAVE A GIRLFRIEND?
DO YOU HAVE A BOYFRIEND?
ARE YOU LYING?
NOT ABOUT THAT.
BREAKFAST OR DINNER?
BRUNCH.
THAT WAS AN INVITATION.
OH.
UM... DINNER, I GUESS.
DINNER IT IS, THEN.
OKAY, FRANCIS, ARE YOU
AND YOUR DRAGON ALL SET?
YEAH, I THINK SO.
AND REGGIE'S
YOUR ASSISTANT, RIGHT?YEAH.
WHO ARE YOU?
ARE YOU
FROM MISS McDERMOTT'S CLASS?
YEAH.
I'M CLASS MONITOR.
[CHILDREN SHOUTING]
OKAY, IT'S FINE.
FRANCIS, SINCE WE'VE GOT
THE KOMODO TO SHOW,
I THINK WE SHOULD--
JUST A SECOND.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
MR. PARKER,
CAN YOU PLEASE CHECK ON
THE COMMOTION IN THERE?
THANK YOU.
THAT'S MY GUY.
THERE'S NO TEACHER IN THERE.
IS ONE OF YOU
THE SECOND GRADE
SUBSTITUTE TEACHER?
YEAH, HE IS.
WHY WOULD YOU
DO THAT TO ME?
I'M DEAD. I WANT
TO BE ENTERTAINED.
WELL, YOU'RE LATE.
THEY'RE GOING TOTALLY A.D.D.
YOU'D BETTER GET
IN THERE NOW.
WHO'S THIS?
SHE'S MY TEACHER'S--
I'M HIS DAUGHTER.MY DAUGHTER.
OH, REALLY?
SHE DOESN'T LOOK ANYTHING
LIKE YOU.
SHE'S SO PALE.
PRACTICALLY A GHOST.
RIGHT. WELL, JUST...GO.
WAS THAT ENTERTAINING
ENOUGH FOR YOU?
IT'S A START, DADDY.
I COULD WEAR A DRESS.
WOULD THAT BE
ENTERTAINING?
I'D ACTUALLY REALLY
LIKE TO SEE THAT.
OH, WELL, MAYBE
WE'LL GO SHOPPING
AFTER THIS.
THAT'D BE FUN,
WOULDN'T IT?
I TOLD YOU TO USE
YOUR FUCKING SIRENS
ON THE WAY OVER.
WE WERE NEARLY LA...
WHAT THE...
HI, GUYS. WELCOME TO
TRAVEL NATIONAL AIR, TNA.
MY TICKET.
I LOVE YOU.
NOW, CAN I GET YOU TWO
A COCKTAIL?
OH...YES.
I WOULD LIKE...
BASICALLY ANYTHING
WITH ONE OF THOSE LITTLE
WOODEN UMBRELLAS IN IT,
YOU KNOW?
NOTHING FOR ME, THANK YOU.
DO THE DAMN REAP FIRST, MASON,
AND THEN GET HAMMERED.
I AM A HIGH-
FUNCTIONING DRUNK.
I AM GOING TO JOIN
THE MILE-HIGH CLUB TODAY.
YOU'VE NEVER HAD
SEX ON A PLANE BEFORE?
WHAT?
IS THAT WHAT THAT MEANS?
MM-HMM.
WHAT DID YOU THINK IT MEANT?
NEVER MIND.
NO, FOR REAL, TELL ME
WHAT YOU THOUGHT IT MEANT.
ROXY, I'VE NEVER FLOWN BEFORE.
I'M A BIT NERVOUS, ALL RIGHT?
WELL, CONGRATULATIONS, BABY.
DRINK UP. BUCKLE UP...
AND DON'T FUCK IT UP.
JUST MAKING THEM DRAW PICTURES
IS A COP-OUT.
YOU SHOULD ACTUALLY
TEACH THEM SOMETHING.
I'M NOT
THEIR TEACHER.
YOU ARE TODAY.
YOU HAVE A CHANCE TO IMPACT
YOUNG PEOPLE'S LIVES,
AND IT'S SLIPPING BY YOU.
IT'S A SHAME.
HOW'S THIS?
OH, IT'S VERY, VERY GOOD.
RULE OF THUMB--
LIP LINER--
YOU WANT TO SKETCH,
HONEY, NOT DRAW,
SKETCH.
THANKS A LOT, DAISY.YEAH.
HI.
HI YOURSELF.
WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO TEACH US?
DISCIPLINE.
RETURN TO YOUR SEAT.
ALL RIGHT,
STOP DRAWING.
I WANT YOU TO LOOK UP AT
THESE FOUR PICTURES UP HERE.
WHAT DO ALL THESE THINGS
HAVE IN COMMON?
YOU.THEY CAN ALL SWIM.
BATS DON'T SWIM.
ANYONE ELSE?
THEY ALL...EAT MEAT?
BEAVERS EAT PLANTS.
ANYONE ELSE?
ANYONE WHO MIGHT GET
INTO COLLEGE?
AND I'M TALKING STATE SCHOOL.
YES?
THEY ALL DIE.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
SARA.
THAT'S RIGHT, SARA,
THEY ALL DIE.
EVERYTHING
AND EVERYONE DIES.
[CLEARS THROAT]
I'M KIDDING.
THEY'RE ALL MAMMALS.
WHO CAN DESCRIBE
THE CHARACTERISTICS
OF A MAMMAL?
YEAH?
THEY CAN ALL FLY.
JESUS, JESSIE, WORK WITH DAISY
ON YOUR LIP GLOSS.
ANYBODY ELSE?
MISS DAISY?
ALL MAMMALS, LIKE PEOPLE,
ARE WARM-BLOODED.
WELL, YES, THEY ARE.
LET'S HEAR IT FOR MISS DAISY.
VERY GOOD.
KIDS ACTUALLY
LIKE YOU, RUBE.
OH, I KNOW.
IT'S BAFFLING, ISN'T IT?
HI. WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
PAYING BILLS.
OH...OH.
THIS WATER BILL
IS AWFULLY HIGH.
YOU AND REGGIE
FLUSH EVERY TIME OUT?
YOU KNOW, MOTHER, I'M LUCKY
IF I EVEN GET TO GO AT ALL.
I'LL BET YOU AND REGGIE
FLUSH TWICE AS MUCH
AS YOU NEED TO.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT, MOM?
PAYING BILLS IS HARD ENOUGH
WITHOUT THE PLAY-BY-PLAY.
I REALLY THINK YOU SHOULD TRY
GETTING OUT OF THE HOUSE.
YOU KNOW, I WAS JUST
THINKING THAT ABOUT YOU.
YOU'RE ALL STRAIGHT LINES
AND RIGHT ANGLES, JOY.
IF YOU DON'T
LOOSEN UP,
YOU'RE NEVER GOING TO HOLD
ANOTHER PENIS AGAIN.
WHY DO YOU KEEP RUNNING AWAY
FROM ME?
WE'LL BE ON OUR WAY
MOMENTARILY,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
WE'RE JUST WAITING
FOR SOME LATE ARRIVALS.
DID YOU BRING YOUR
SUNSCREEN, ROXY?
I'M BLACK.OH, RIGHT.
BLACK PEOPLE TAN, YOU BOZO.
I HAVE SPF 15
IF YOU WANT TO USE IT.
CHAMPAGNE?
AH, YES.
UH, NO, THANK YOU.
MISSY, YOU LOOK
SO FAMILIAR TO ME.
WHAT'S YOUR LAST NAME?
BALABANIAN. IT'S ARMENIAN.
OH, MY MISTAKE.
NICE BRACELET.
OH, IT WAS MY GRANDMOTHER'S.
WOW, IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
THANK YOU.
I LOVE THAT ARMENIAN
CRAFTSMANSHIP.
I WILL HAVE
THAT CHAMPAGNE NOW.
OKAY.GOOD FOR YOU, ROXY.
FINALLY LETTING GO
AND RELAXING.
THAT'S A DAMN SHAME.WHAT IS?
THAT PRETTY ARMENIAN GIRL
IS GOING TO DIE
LOOKING
LIKE AN IN-FLIGHT HOOKER.
HMM, AT LEAST
SHE GOT TO SEE THE WORLD.
LOOKING LIKE A HOOKER.
THERE YOU GO.
THANK YOU.
I SEEM TO HAVE
DROPPED MY TICKET
ON THE FLOOR.
I'M REALLY--
I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I JUST...
THERE YOU GO, CLUMSY.
AND AT LEAST
I GOT TO SEE THAT.
YOU'RE TRAGIC.
I SUPPOSE I AM.
[BURPS]
OKAY, EVERYONE,
SETTLE DOWN, PLEASE.
WE HAVE SOMETHING VERY SPECIAL
TO SHARE WITH YOU TODAY,
A VERY SPECIAL REPORT
ON THE KOMODO DRAGON
BY FRANCIS BISCHETTI.
"THE KOMODO DRAGON,
OR  VARANUS KOMODOENSIS,"
BY FRANCIS BISCHETTI.
THE KOMODO
IS FOUND EXCLUSIVELY
ON THE INDONESIAN ISLANDS
OF KOMODO,
RINTJA, PADAR, GILI, AND MOTA.
IT HUNTS BY AMBUSH
AND SEIZES WITH ITS JAWS.
DRAGON KILLS JANITOR.
POSSIBILITY.
IT CAN BITE A MAN'S HAND
RIGHT OFF.
THEY LIVE FREE IN THE WILD,
BEHOLDEN TO NO MAN.
[SCREAMS]
OH, MY GOD.
THAT'S US.
WHAT IN THE NAME OF JESUS?
GO BACK TO HELL, YOU BEAST.
YOU WON'T TOUCH MY CHILDREN.
DON'T HURT FRODO!
I GOT IT.
DID THEY CATCH IT?
FI--FIRE DRILL.
FIRE DRILL,
TWO LINES OUT THE DOOR.
DAMN.
DID I KILL
SOMETHING ENDANGERED?
YOU DID.
SHIT. I'M A MEMBER
OF THE SIERRA CLUB.
WELL...IT WAS IN SELF-DEFENSE.
YEAH.
IT'S NOT LIKE
IT WAS SOMETHING CUTE,
LIKE A BABY SEAL.
THERE YOU GO.
THIS LOOKS PROMISING.
WHY?NEWLYWEDS--
ACCIDENT PRONE,
OBVIOUSLY.
OKAY, THERE YOU GO.
THANKS, MISSY.
OH, I'VE GOT
NO UMBRELLA?
THEY'RE A SECURITY RISK.
YOU CAN'T BE
TOO CAREFUL.
CAN YOU?
WHAT'S THE MOVIE?
FOUR WEDDINGS AND A FUNERAL.
CLOSE ENOUGH.
HEY, WAIT!
WHY ARE YOU
STALKING ME?
YOU'RE THE STALKER.
GO AWAY.
WHY DID YOU
TOUCH THAT DRAGON?
I'M A DRAGON SLAYER.
NOW GO AWAY.
I SAW YOU STEAL
FROM THAT GIRL.
GOOD FOR YOU.
WANT SOME
CHOCOLATE MILK?
SURE.
AREN'T YOU GOING
TO GET IN TROUBLE
FOR DITCHING SCHOOL?
AREN'T YOU?
I DON'T HAVE SCHOOL.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU DO
ALL DAY?
I'M A DRAGON SLAYER.
I TOLD YOU.
NOW STOP FOLLOWING ME.
DO YOU KNOW A GIRL
NAMED GEORGE?
WAS SHE KILLED
BY A TOILET SEAT?
YEAH, I'VE HEARD OF HER.
YOU'RE A BRAVE GIRL.
SO GEORGE STAYS IN,
I SUSPECT,
WITH NOTHING.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO
MISS MR. HESBURGH
WHEN HE SHOWS UP.
I TOLD YOU
I'D POINT HIM OUT TO YOU
WHEN HE COMES IN OFF THE 18th.
I BET FIVE BUCKS.
FIVE BUCKS?
WHERE ARE WE, VEGAS?
WELL, THAT'S THE GLORY
OF POKER.
MY DAD ALWAYS SAYS,
"IT HAS TO HURT A LITTLE BIT."
OTHERWISE,
BETS DON'T MATTER,
SO, GEORGE,
ARE YOU GOING TO CALL,
RAISE, OR FOLD?
FOLD.
HMM...MISTAKE.
I HAD A PAIR OF KINGS.
WELL, ACTUALLY,
YOU HAD TRIP KINGS.
TWO IN THE POCKET
AND ONE SHOWING
ON THE BOARD.
IT'S THREE KINGS...
TRIPS.
[GEORGE]:  TRIP, TRIP, TRIP,
YOU ARE REALLY CUTE.
YOU BLUFFED ME.
YEAH, IT'S THE STORY
OF MY LIFE.
SIR.
HOW IS EVERYTHING?
IT'S LOVELY. HOW ARE YOU?
LOVELY, AND YOU, MISS?
LOVELY.
[GEORGE]:  ENOUGH
WITH THE FUCKING "LOVELY."
TALK LIKE MEN.
THE GOLF COURSE HAS
NEVER BEEN IN BETTER SHAPE.
IF WE COULD JUST GET
OLD MAN GIBSON
TO STOP DRIVING HIS CART
THROUGH THE SAND TRAPS.
GOOD ONE, SIR.
CALL ME IF YOU NEED ANYTHING.
[GEORGE]:  YEAH, IF HE NEEDS
SOMEONE FURTHER UP HIS ASS.
YOU KNOW, FOR SOMEONE
WHO SUPPOSEDLY HATES
COUNTRY CLUB LIFE,
YOU SEEM PRETTY COMFORTABLE.
I HATE IT.
WHY?
ABSOLUTELY NO SURPRISES.
I HEAR THE SAME NONSENSE
EVERY TIME I WALK IN--
"ISN'T THAT A LOVELY DRESS?"
"MAN, THE 14th JUST ATE ME UP
TODAY."
"ANOTHER BOMBAY MARTINI, SIR?"
IT'S LIKE YOU KNOW
EVERYTHING
EVERYONE'S GOING TO DO
BEFORE THEY DO IT.
EXCEPT FOR THAT.
WE STILL HAVE FOUR PLANES
AHEAD OF US,
BUT UNTIL WE GET
OFF THE GROUND,
MISSY AND SPARKLE
WILL BE HAPPY TO DISTRACT YOU.
OPEN YOUR BAG,
OPEN YOUR BAG.
CONCENTRATE ON
YOUR POST-IT, MASON.
MAYBE I'M NOT
A VERY GOOD FLIER.
YOU'RE NOT A VERY GOOD REAPER.
MRS...
TANYA DILLER.
BERNARD...
DILLER.
WHICH ONE
DO YOU LIKE BEST?
OH, BOTH OF THEM.
[LAUGHS]
CAN I OFFER YOU
A SNACK?
NO, GET THOSE PEANUTS
FAR AWAY FROM MY BABY.
HE'S TOTALLY ALLERGIC.
ALWAYS LOOKING
OUT FOR ME, BABE.
LOVE YOU.LOVE YOU MORE.
BERNARD DILLER,
IT'S BERNARD DILLER.
HE'S DEAD.
GOOD, BECAUSE I CAN'T STAND
WATCHING THAT TONSIL HOCKEY
ALL THE WAY TO CANCUN.
I CAN.
BUSTED.
MORE CHAMPAGNE, PLEASE.
ACCOUNT NUMBER 1835.
YOU'RE A QUICK
STUDY, GEORGE...
WHO HAS NO LAST NAME.I HAVE ONE.
YOU'RE JUST NOT
A CLEVER ENOUGH REPORTER
TO FIGURE IT OUT.
WHO SAID I WAS A REPORTER?
SO YOU DON'T WRITE
FOR THE NEWSPAPER?
YOU WERE LYING TO ME.
I WORK FOR THE NEWSPAPER,
BUT I'M NOT A REPORTER.
I ACTUALLY WRITE
OBITS.
I READ OBITS.
I WRITE THEM.I READ THEM.
WELL, WE HAVE THAT
IN COMMON, THEN.
DEATH-FIXATED.
NO WAY.
DEATHS CELEBRATE LIFE,
A LIFE SO WELL LIVED
THAT IT NEEDS
TO BE WRITTEN ABOUT.
[GEORGE]:  I REALLY LIKE HIM.
I REALLY LIKE YOU.
ANYTHING ELSE, MR. HESBURGH?
UH, NO.
THANKS.
WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU'RE T. HESBURGH?
YES...I AM.
I'M SORRY.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY FUCKING GOD.
HEY, WAIT A SECOND.
GEORGE.
HEY, GEORGE, WAIT.
LOOK, I SHOULD HAVE TOLD YOU
MY NAME WAS HESBURGH,
BUT I WAS JUST
HAVING SOME FUN.
JUST STAY AWAY
FROM ME, JUST STAY--
NO, WAIT.
WAIT A SECOND.
I WASN'T MESSING WITH YOU.
I MEAN, I GUESS
I WAS AT FIRST,
BUT...I REALLY DO LIKE YOU.
I REALLY LIKE YOU TOO.
[GEORGE]:
JUST DO THE JOB, GEORGE.
AS I LIVE AND BREATHE,
THOMAS HESBURGH III.
WHAT?
HEY, DAD.
WHO ARE YOU?
I'M THOMAS HESBURGH III.
I'M THE THIRD...TRIP.
I KNOW,
BUT THAT'S THE HAND I WAS
DEALT. THANKS A LOT, DAD.
HI, AND I'M THOMAS HESBURGH.
HI.
SO YOU'RE THREE.
THEN YOU'RE...
JUNIOR.
YOU CAN PUT ALL
THE BLAME ON ME.
MY FATHER WAS
THOMAS HESBURGH,
I'M THOMAS HESBURGH,
TRIP IS
THOMAS HESBURGH,
AND WHEN HE GETS AROUND
TO SIRING A SON,
THE KID WILL BE SADDLED
WITH...
PETER, PETER,
PUMPKIN EATER.
GOOD FOR YOU.
OH, DAD, THIS IS
MY FRIEND, GEORGE.
GEORGE, THIS IS MY DAD.
A PLEASURE.
IS EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT,
YOUNG LADY?
JUST TOO MUCH, UM, CHAMPAGNE.
AH.
SON OF A...
LOOK AT THIS.
HELENE!
WATCH OUT.
HELENE, WATCH--
DAD?
OH, MY GOD, DAD.
SAY SOMETHING.
SAY SOMETHING,
DAD, PLEASE.
PLEASE, DON'T DO THIS.
[GEORGE]:  AND JUST LIKE THAT,
TRIP ESCAPED.
I WONDER IF HE WOULD'VE
SEEN IT THAT WAY.
DAD?
ON BEHALF OF TNA,
I DO APOLOGIZE FOR OUR DELAY.
WE'RE EXPERIENCING
SOME FLOW CONTROL
BECAUSE OF THE WEATHER.
IN THE MEANTIME, PLEASE ENJOY
A REFRESHING COCKTAIL.
I KNOW I AM...
I'M KIDDING. NO, I'M NOT.
WE ARE GOING TO
CANCUN TODAY, ROXY.
HELL, YEAH.
WE ARE GOING TO DRINK
MARGARITAS ON THE BEACH.
HELLO.
[GIGGLING]
IT'S ON.
I COULD USE SOME MORE BUBBLY.
HI.
HOW WAS SCHOOL TODAY?
A DRAGON WAS KILLED...
WOW.
AND I THINK
OUR JANITOR WAS HURT.
HOW?
TRYING TO CATCH THE DRAGON.
OKAY.
AND I TALKED TO THIS BOY.
WELL, THAT'S NICE.
WAS HE CUTE?
I THINK HE KNOWS GEORGE.
SO...IT WAS
A BUSY DAY.
[MOANING]
I CAN'T WAIT FOR SOME
REAL MEXICAN FOOD.
DO YOU LIKE
MOLE SAUCE?
"MOL-AY,"
AND IT'S MY FAVORITE.
YOU KNOW IT'S REAL
CHOCOLATE SAUCE?
FUCK OFF.MM-HMM.
[CHOKING]
HELP!
I WANTED TO GO
SNORKELING.
IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL
DOWN THERE.
ALL THE DIFFERENT FISH,
IT'S LIKE ANOTHER WORLD.
HELP!
FUCKING PEANUTS.
I CAN'T...BREATHE.
I WANTED TO TRY
PARASAILING, TOO.
A HUNDRED FEET IN THE AIR
WITH YOUR BALLS IN A SLING
BEHIND A MOTORBOAT DRIVEN
BY TWO DRUNKS NAMED PEDRO?
I DON'T THINK SO.
[SCREAMING]
CAN YOU SEE?
I CAN'T SEE.IS HE ALL RIGHT?
BERNIE.
BABY?
YOU BITCH.
[SCREAMING]
MAYBE THE TICKETS
ARE REFUNDABLE.
ACT OF GOD,
ALL THAT BULL,
YOU KNOW?
MAYBE.MAYBE.
IT SHOULD JUST BE
A COUPLE MORE MINUTES, FOLKS.
THANKS FOR YOUR PATIENCE.
COME ON, DAD.LOOK AT HIM.
DON'T DO THIS.
HE LEARNED LIFESAVING
AT JUNIOR LIFEGUARDS.
HE REALLY LOVES YOU.
HE LIKES YOU.
I'VE SEEN THE WAY
HE LOOKS AT YOU.
SOMETHING
GOING ON THERE.
I DON'T...IT WAS
JUST FLIRTING.
I SHOULDN'T
HAVE BEEN DOING IT.
SAY GOODBYE TO MY SON,
WHY DON'T YOU?
UM, HE'S...BUSY
WITH YOU.
DON'T BE AFRAID.
WELL, SAY SOMETHING.
TELL HIM
YOU'RE SORRY.
GOD...OKAY.
[GEORGE]:  I LIKE HIM.
DO I SAY, "I'LL CALL YOU"?
OR DO I JUST GIVE HIM
MY NUMBER?
THAT'S WHAT DAISY WOULD DO.
SHE'D SAY, "HERE'S MY CARD."
FUCK, HIS DAD JUST DIED.
I...
I'M JUST SORRY.
I'LL LOOK OUT
FOR HIM.
COME ON, PLEASE.
YOU LOOK OUT
FOR HIM, TOO, HUH?
OKAY.
PROMISE?
I PROMISE.
HI.
DID YOU GET REGGIE?YES.
COME ON, LEAVE THAT FOR LATER.
I'LL BUY YOU
AN ICE CREAM.
YOU USED TO LOVE
RAINBOW SHERBET, RIGHT?
WE NEED TO CHAT ABOUT REGGIE.
HER ISSUES ARE REALLY BURIED.
I'M DEALING WITH HER ISSUES,
MOM.
I STOPPED USING
TOP AND BOTTOM SHEETS.
I JUST TAKE
A BIG NAVAJO BLANKET,
TOSS IT OVER THE FUTON,
BOOM, BED'S MADE.WELL, THAT'S GREAT.
THE NEXT TIME
I GO CAMPING WITH TONTO,
I'LL BE SURE
TO GIVE THAT A SHOT.
I DON'T THINK
CONVENTIONAL THERAPY
IS THE WAY TO GO, JOY.
MY WORD, YOU'RE MAKING
THIS BED SO TIGHT.
YOU KNOW, MOM, IT'S MY BED,
AND I'M MAKING IT
THE WAY THAT I LIKE,
BECAUSE I'M GOING
TO LIE IN IT.
TRUER WORDS
WERE NEVER SPOKEN.
NO, YOU KNOW WHAT'S TRUE?
YOU WOULD RATHER
STAND HERE
AND CRITICIZE
HOW I MAKE MY BED
THAN ACTUALLY
HELP ME MAKE IT.
YOUR IDEA OF HELP
IS TRYING TO KEEP ORDER.
SOMETIMES ORDER
IS NOT POSSIBLE, JOY.
IT IS NOT
ALWAYS POSSIBLE
TO MAKE SURE
THAT EVERYTHING...
IS IN THE PROPER PLACE.
OKAY, "HEY, SHOULD I CALL
MY HUSBAND AND DAUGHTER
"AND TELL THEM
WHERE I AM?
"NO, I THINK
I'LL JUST SEND THEM
"SOME SMOKE SIGNALS
FROM MY TEEPEE"!
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
YOU ARE SO FUCKING SELFISH.
"HEY, TIME.
WHO NEEDS TIME, RIGHT?
I'M A FREE SPIRIT.
I AM WAY BEYOND TIME."
"LET'S KEEP EVERYTHING
NEAT AND TIDY.
"LET'S MAKE SURE
"THAT EVERYTHING
IS IN ITS PROPER PLACE,
IS EXACTLY WHERE I LEFT IT,
"THAT NOTHING
WILL EVER CHANGE.
"MY MARRIAGE CAN END,
MY DAUGHTER CAN DIE,
BUT THANK GOD
THE HOUSE IS NEAT."
GO TO HELL!
GODDAMMIT, JOY!
SOMETIMES LIFE IS MESSY!
GET USED TO IT!
HI, SWEETIE.
HOW WAS SCHOOL?
GOOD.
SO...WHO'S UP FOR ICE CREAM?
DID YOU KNOW
THAT DUE TO THE KOMODO
DRAGON'S SPEED,
IT IS NEARLY
IMPOSSIBLE TO ESCAPE
IF IT'S CHASING YOU?
THINKING ABOUT
GETTING A PET?
JUST LEARNING
SOMETHING NEW.
KIFFANY, ARE THERE
ANY OF THOSE FRESH
OATMEAL COOKIES LEFT?
I THINK SO.WILL YOU BRING ONE
FOR MY FRIEND HERE?
WILL YOU WARM IT UP, PLEASE?
ALL RIGHT.THANK YOU.
I FEEL SOMETHING BAD COMING.
WHAT MAKES YOU
SAY THAT?
ANY TIME YOU ORDER ME FOOD,
YOU ALWAYS FOLLOW IT UP
WITH BAD NEWS.
HOW WAS
THE MONTGOMERY CLUB?
FINE.
TELL ME THE BAD NEWS.
THERE'S NO BAD NEWS,
GEORGE.
I JUST WANT
TO LEAVE MY GIRL...
WITH A SMILE ON HER FACE.
WHAT'S UP WITH HIM?I'M NOT SURE.
WE WERE AT A SCHOOL TODAY.
HE ACTS REALLY STRANGE
AROUND KIDS.
HMM.
STRANGER.
HOW WAS THE MONTGOMERY CLUB?
STUFFY, ENTITLED,
BULLSHIT.
I REALLY LIKED IT.
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
I THINK I'M GOING
TO GO BACK.
MM-HMM, WHAT'S HIS NAME?
TRIP.
TRIP?
HERE YOU GO,
SWEETHEART.THANK YOU, KIFFANY.
TRIP...
I KISSED HIM,
AND THEN
I REAPED HIS DAD.
COMPLICATED.
GOOD KISSER?
HMM, SMART, FUNNY...
MONEY?
PLEASE.
UP UNTIL HIS DAD DIED,
I THOUGHT HE WAS GOING TO
BE MY FIRST BOYFRIEND.
MM-HMM, AND NOW?
HE'S MY FIRST BOYFRIEND.
WELL...IT'S A LITTLE RISKY,
GEORGIA.
WHAT HAVE
I GOT TO LOSE?
EVERYTHING.
I BET EVERYTHING.
OH, WELL,
THEN YOU SAY,
"ALL IN."
ALL IN.RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, TOO RICH
FOR MY BLOOD.
I FOLD.
LET'S SEE.
OH...
OH, WOW.
YOU WIN, YOU WIN.
HERE, HERE. YAY!
UM...
I THINK IT'S YOUR BEDTIME,
REGGIE.
IF YOU WANT TO STAY UP
A LITTLE WHILE LONGER, HONEY,
IT'S OKAY WITH ME.
THAT'S OKAY.
I'M TIRED.
I HAD A LONG DAY.
SEE YOU IN THE MORNING.'NIGHT.
GOOD NIGHT, HONEY.
JOY, HONEY?
HMM?
I THINK I'LL GO HOME TOMORROW.
REALLY?
MM-HMM.
WE NEVER DO SEEM
TO FIND A RESTING PLACE,
DO WE?
NO.
I DON'T MEAN
TO BE HURTFUL, MOM.
NEITHER DO I.
I KNOW.
I COULD ALWAYS COME BACK.
HMM...
SAY IT.
YOU CAN ALWAYS COME BACK.
THANK YOU.
I WORRY...ABOUT YOUR DAUGHTER.
I KNOW.
BOTH OF THEM.
[GEORGE]:  I THINK THAT
EVERYONE WANTS TO ESCAPE
WHEREVER THEY ARE.
WE NEARLY MADE IT.
TO OUR NEAR ESCAPE.
CLINK.
I THINK IT WAS MEANT
TO BE A NARROW ESCAPE,
ACTUALLY, ROXY.
TO THAT TOO.
CLINK.
CLINK, YEAH.
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN
TO MEXICO?
NO.
I'VE NEVER BEEN
ANYWHERE.
I THINK IT WOULD HAVE
BEEN NICE.
ME TOO.
I THINK WE WOULD HAVE
HAD FUN.
ME TOO.
[GEORGE]:  PEOPLE DON'T SEEM
REALLY HAPPY WHERE THEY ARE.
THEY'RE ALWAYS LOOKING
FOR A DIFFERENT PLACE,
A DIFFERENT PERSON,
JUST DIFFERENT.
LIKE MY MOM USED TO SAY,
"THE GRASS
IS ALWAYS GREENER..."
EVERYONE'S SEARCHING
FOR THE OTHER SIDE.
I'M ALREADY THERE,
AND I'M STILL LOOKING.
WE'RE SORRY.
YOUR CALL CANNOT BE
COMPLETED AS DIALED.
PLEASE CHECK THE NUMBER
AND DIAL AGAIN, OR CALL...
[GEORGE]:
NO ONE WILL ADMIT IT,
BUT PEOPLE DESPERATELY WANT
TO BE IN CLUBS,
ESPECIALLY THE ONES
THEY CAN'T JOIN,
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO
NOW THAT I'VE FOUND THE ONE
I WANT TO BELONG TO...
SO I WENT BACK TO THE ONLY ONE
THAT WOULD HAVE ME
FOR A MEMBER.
ARE YOU STILL WAITING
FOR YOUR FRIENDS, HON?
YEAH.
I'LL COME BACK.
[GEORGE]:  AND JUST BECAUSE
I HAD NO ONE TO TALK TO,
DIDN'T MEAN I COULDN'T LISTEN.
[RINGS]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
I'LL GET IT.
HELLO?
LASS RESIDENCE.
YOU MOTHER TELLS ME YOU'RE
NOT GOING BACK TO COLLEGE
NEXT SEMESTER.
YEAH.
CONGRATULATIONS.
A FROG?
MM-HMM.
A LITTLE "YOU'RE ON
YOUR OWN" PRESENT.
FOR LUCK?
FROGS SYMBOLIZE
NEW LIFE,
TRANSFORMATION,
FROM TADPOLE
TO YOUNG WOMAN...
THAT'S YOU,
SWEETHEART.
WHATEVER
YOU SAY, GRANDMA.
YOU HAVE GREAT LIFE
IN YOU, GEORGIA.
DON'T LET THAT
ESCAPE YOU.
PROMISE?
I PROMISE.
IT'S A FILTHY HABIT.
ONE DRAG, AND DON'T
TELL YOUR MOTHER.
I PROMISE.
HELLO?
HELLO?CAN I HELP YOU?
HI. THIS IS...
IS THIS THE
LADY OF THE HOUSE?
NO, THE LADY
OF THE HOUSE
IS DOING SOMETHING
EXTREMELY IMPORTANT.
I THINK IT INVOLVES
A DUST BUSTER.
WHO IS THIS?
I HAVE THE WRONG NUMBER.
[GEORGE]:  AS A LITTLE GIRL,
I USED TO THINK
MY GRANDMA WAS A LITTLE LOONY.
NOW I GET THAT SHE WAS
JUST REALLY ALIVE.
IF I ONLY KNEW THEN
WHAT I KNOW NOW...
[CHUCKLES]
JOIN THE CLUB.