[♪♪]
[BUZZING]
[GEORGE]  EVERY FAMILY
HAS ITS MORNING RITUALS.
I KNOW MINE DID.
THE GUN WENT OFF AT 7:00,
RISE AND SHINE.
ACTUALLY,
WE WERE NEVER THAT BIG
ON THE SHINE, BUT...
WHAT I REALLY REMEMBER
ABOUT MORNING...
WAS COFFEE--
THE SMELL OF IT,
THE SOUNDS OF IT...
EVERYONE IN MY FAMILY
LOVED COFFEE.
THIS SOUNDS WEIRD,
BUT SOMETIMES I THINK
IT'S THE ONE THING
WE ALL LOVED.
CAN I SEE THE OBITS?
MORE COFFEE?
PLEASE.
IT'S MY GUY.
THAT'S THE GUY I KISSED.
HE'S OLD. AND DEAD.
THE GUY I KISSED
ISN'T DEAD.
THAT'S HIS DAD.
I REAPED HIS DAD.
AND HIS MEMORIAL SERVICE
IS TODAY AT 3:00.
WEAR SOMETHING BLACK
AND SHORT.
REALLY? YOU THINK
I SHOULD GO?
ABSOLUTELY.
POINT GREY CLUB.
MM. ELEGANT.
MAYBE SOMETHING...
BLACK AND LONG.
WHAT'S THAT EXPRESSION?
"DON'T SHIT WHERE YOU EAT.
DON'T SHIT WHERE YOU REAP?"
I'M DEFINITELY
NOT GOING.
I'M GOING TO HELP YOU
PICK OUT AN OUTFIT.
YEAH. PLEASE.
BONJOUR.
WHAT'S IN THE BAG?
CINNAMON BUNS.
MM!FEEL FREE.
THEY'RE STILL WARM.MM!
I DO LOVE ME
A TASTY CINNAMON BUN.
MM. I'M SO GLAD
I'M DONE FOR TODAY,
I SWEAR.
YOU HAD TO REAP
THIS MORNING?
YEAH.
THAT FROSTING APPLICATOR,
A DANGEROUS BLOODY MACHINE,
THAT IS.
IT TOOK THE GUY'S HAND
CLEAN OFF.
WELL, THE HAND
STRAIGHT OFF.
HE DIED OF BLOOD LOSS.
OR SHOCK.
SOMETHING.
CAN'T REMEMBER.
ANYWAY, REALLY, REALLY,
REALLY, REALLY,
REALLY BLOODY DEATH.
THAT'S DISGUSTING.
WHAT?
OH, DON'T BE
SUCH SISSIES.
THESE ONES
ARE CLEAN.
I WIPED THE BLOOD
OFF OF THEM ONES.
YOU'RE DISGUSTING.
ANYTHING INTERESTING
IN THE OBITS?
NOPE, JUST
THE USUAL CRAP--
CHERISHED SCHOOLMASTER,
BELOVED AUNT,
DEAD CONSTRUCTION WORKER.
FOR YOU, MY DEAR.
AND YOU, MY FRIEND.
4:00?
THAT A PROBLEM?NO. IT'S JUST...
IT'S JUST...
A GIRL HAS A LIFE.
FOR EXAMPLE?
GIRL STUFF.
WELL...
SINCE THIS IS NOT A FACIAL,
BUT THE END OF
A PERSON'S LIFE,
I DON'T THINK
IT CAN BE RESCHEDULED.
YOU'RE A SMART GIRL,
GEORGE.
JUGGLE THINGS.
I CAN JUGGLE THINGS.
ONE...
DEUX...
UH, THREE.
AHEM. READY?
[MASON HUMMING]
WHOO-OO-HOO.
YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
ACTUALLY,
THESE CINNAMON BUNS
STARTED OFF TO BE
A VERY NICE GESTURE, RUBE,
AND WHAT I WANTED TO DO
IS GET PEOPLE BREAKFAST,
AND THAT'S WHAT I GET.
DAISY, BACK ME UP.
YOUR HEART'S
IN THE RIGHT PLACE.
YOUR HEART'S NOT
THE HEART IS NOT,
AS IS SO OFTEN SEEN
ON TELEVISION,
IN THE CENTER OF THE BODY.
BUT THANK YOU, AUDREY.
OKAY, WHO WOULD LIKE
TO GO NEXT?
WHO WOULD LIKE TO SHOW
THEIR MODEL OF THE HEART?
FRANCIS?EXCELLENT.
YOU'RE GOING
TO LIKE THIS, REGGIE.
OKAY.
BEFORE I BEGIN,
I WOULD JUST WANT
TO SAY THANK YOU
FOR THE TRIBUTE
TO MY DEAD KOMODO DRAGON,
WHO WAS TRAGICALLY KILLED
LAST WEEK DURING SCHOOL.
I'M SURE FRODO'S
IN HEAVEN, FRANCIS.
ALTHOUGH THERE'S NO
SCIENTIFIC EVIDENCE
TO SUPPORT THAT,
MRS. RICKET,
THANKS.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
WHENEVER YOU'RE READY,
FRANCIS.
"THE HUMAN HEART,"
BY FRANCIS BISCHETTI.
MY FIRST ATTEMPT
AT MODELLING THE HEART
USING DRY MACARONI
WAS A DISASTER.
THE RIGHT VENTRICLE
KEPT FALLING OFF.
SO WHAT YOU ARE ABOUT TO SEE,
I HAVE ENTITLED "THE HEART--
2.0"
OH, COOL.
UH, FRANCIS, WHERE--
WHERE DID YOU GET THAT?
THE INTERNET.
IS IT FROM AN ANIMAL?
IT JUST SAID "HEART"
ON THE WEBSITE.
IT WAS FROM
AN INTERNATIONAL MAIL CODE.
RWANDA, I BELIEVE.
UH, FRANCIS, THE, UH,
THE ASSIGNMENT WAS
TO MAKE A MODEL
OF THE HEART,
NOT, UH, TO BUY ONE.
UH, REGGIE?
I BELIEVE YOU'RE NEXT.
I DON'T HAVE IT.
OKAY...
AND, UH, WHY DON'T YOU
HAVE IT?
WELL...HER DOG ATE IT!
YEAH, UM... YEAH.
THAT'LL TEACH YOU
TO MAKE A HEART OUT OF LIVER.
EVERYBODY KNOWS
DOGS LIKE LIVER.
IS THAT WHAT HAPPENED,
REGGIE?
YEAH. MY DOG ATE IT.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
OKAY.
REGGIE, I'LL GIVE YOU
UNTIL TOMORROW.
COFFEE'S NICE
THIS MORNING.
TASTES THE SAME TO ME.
DID YOU MAKE IT
THIS MORNING, CRYSTAL?
DO ANYTHING DIFFERENT?
DIFFERENT BEANS?
BOTTLED WATER?
COLD DRIP?
HMM. TASTES DIFFERENT.
MAYBE YOU'RE THE ONE
THAT'S DIFFERENT.
YOU KNOW WHAT, MISTY?
I THINK YOU'RE THE ONE
THAT'S DIFFERENT.
OH, DID I TELL YOU
FRED ASKED ME OUT
LAST WEEK FOR COFFEE.
AND?
WELL, I DON'T WANT
TO HAVE SEX WITH FRED.
IT'S JUST COFFEE.
COFFEE'S CODE, MILLIE.
FRED WANTS ME.
HE WANTS A DOUBLE-SHOT
OF MISTY...
EXTRA FOAM.
YOU KNOW...
MISTY, SOMETIMES
COFFEE IS JUST COFFEE.
I WORK HERE 35 HOURS A WEEK,
AND I SWEAR TO GOD,
I SPEND 34 OF THEM
THINKING ABOUT SEX.
AND THE OTHER HOUR?
OH, I'M HAVING SEX.
YOU'RE SO FULL
OF SHIT, MISTY.
QUE PASA,JULIO?
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
YOU HAD SEX, MILLIE?
NEVER?
OH, IT'S BEEN A WHILE.
WHAT ARE YOU LADIES
TALKING ABOUT?
COFFEE.
I COULD USE
A NICE CUP OF COFFEE MYSELF,
RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
[MAN GROANING]
[GROANS]
OH, I CAN'T FEEL MY ARM.
STAN?
STAN! SAY SOMETHING.
OH, MY LORD.
HE'S HAVING A CORONARY.
IS HE GONNA DIE?
MAMA, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
DON'T LOOK AT ME.
I DON'T HAVE HIS POST-IT.
ALL RIGHT, HAPPY TIME,
LIFE-SUPPORT PLAN.
CODE BLUE.
PEOPLE, MAN YOUR POSTS.
ON THE DOUBLE!
MILLIE!
UH, I WASN'T HERE
THAT DAY.
COME ON, PEOPLE!
WHERE'S MY
DEFIBRILLATOR CREW?
THERE'S CHEESE ON THESE!
WHO HAS BEEN MAKING
GRILLED-CHEESE SANDWICHES
WITH THE DEFIBRILLATOR
PADDLES?
CONGRATULATIONS, HAPPY TIME.
YOU JUST
KILLED A MAN.
THANK YOU, STAN.
YOU KNOW, I'M REALLY
DISAPPOINTED, PEOPLE.
WE HAD C.P.R. TRAINING
LAST MONTH,
AND WE'RE DOING IT AGAIN
TOMORROW MORNING, MANDATORY.
IT'S A LITTLE UNSETTLING
GETTING THAT CLOSE TO DEATH,
ISN'T IT?
MM. NOT SO MUCH.
I THINK GEORGE
IS IN LOVE.
SHE TELL YOU THAT?
NO. SHE DIDN'T HAVE TO.
UNLIKE YOU, I CAN
SENSE THESE THINGS.
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY?
I HAVE KEEN INTUITION.
OH, YOU WISH YOU HAD
MY INTUITION.
OH, ROXY,
IT'S NOT A CONTEST.
I GOT TO HOP,
GOT A SOUL TO TAKE.
I KNOW THIS ADDRESS.
THAT'S THE MILLSTONE HOTEL.
REALLY?
WELL, HOW FUN.
I LOVE HOTELS.
MAYBE I'LL DRESS UP
AS A HOUSEKEEPER.
WHY AREN'T YOU WEARING
YOUR CROSS ANYMORE?
I LOST IT.
YOUR FAITH OR THE CROSS?
BOTH.
I WAS JUST PLAYING THE PART
OF THE NICE CATHOLIC GIRL.
I'M NOT,
I'M NOT THE REAL THING.
NO?
THE SPIRITUAL THING
ISN'T ME.
I'M AN ACTRESS.
I'M JUST A REALLY
GOOD ACTRESS.
WHATEVER YOU SAY, DAISY.
DAISY ADAIR.
SO OUR LITTLE GEORGIE IS
CRASHING A MEMORIAL SERVICE
TO CHASE A BOY?
YEAH. SHE WON'T ACTUALLY GO.
NO?SHE'LL CHICKEN OUT.
I HAVE THE MILLSTONE REAP,
AND SHE'S TOO AFRAID
TO GO ALONE.
[MAN] THIS WAY, PLEASE.
NO, REALLY NOT
MY CROWD.
YOU AND ME BOTH, PAL.
YOU COULDN'T FALL
FOR A NICE WORKING MAN,
COULD YOU?
YOU HAD TO FIND
A BLOODY ARISTOCRAT.
HE WORKS.
HE'S A JOURNALIST.
HAH, WORKS?
FOR HIS RICH, DEAD
FATHER'S NEWSPAPER--
CHA-CHING!
CAN YOU JUST TRY
TO BEHAVE YOURSELF
AND ACT
LIKE A GENTLEMAN?
FUCK OFF.
OKAY, FINE.
HOW DO I LOOK?
ACTUALLY,
YOU LOOK REALLY NICE.
VERY "COME HITHER."
OOH.GOOD.
SO WHICH ONE IS HE?
THE GOOD-LOOKING
GUY IN BLACK.
MM. YES. STILL NOT CLEAR.
THAT ONE.
I REALLY LIKE HIM,
SO DON'T SCREW THIS UP.
I WON'T.
GEORGE, WHY AM I HERE?
TO PAY YOUR RESPECTS
TO HIS FATHER,
THOMAS HESBURGH.
OKAY, GOT IT.
AND WHY ARE YOU HERE?
TO PAY MY RESPECTS
TO HIS FATHER.
THOMAS HESBURGH.
OH, MY GOD.
YOU REAPED
HIS FATHER.
NOW YOU WANT TO
SNOG HIS SON.
HAH.
I DON'T KNOW. I JUST...
LOOK, I HAVE ONE HOUR
BEFORE MY REAP, SO WHATEVER.
OH, LET'S
SYNCHRONIZE WATCHES.
GOOD IDEA.
I DON'T HAVE A WATCH.
[JOY]
IT'S ALMOST TIME TO GO.
I DON'T WANT
TO GO TO DAD'S TONIGHT.
YOU HAVE TO.
WHY?
BECAUSE
IT'S COURT-ORDERED.
DO YOU HAVE ANY
HOMEWORK FOR TONIGHT?
I SORT OF DIDN'T FINISH
THAT BIOLOGY PROJECT.
THE HEART MODEL?
I THOUGHT THAT WAS
DUE TODAY.
IT WAS, BUT...
BUT WHAT?
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO
WITH ALL THE PAPIER-MACHE
I BOUGHT, HMM?
PUT IT IN THE BASEMENT?
ALONG WITH YOUR DRUM SET
AND YOUR RIDING CLOTHES?
THE TEENAGE GRAVEYARD.
IT'S NOT A GRAVEYARD.
I KNOW.
IT'S JUST AN EXPRESSION.
MRS. RICKET SAID
I COULD HAVE MORE TIME.
HMM.
THAT WAS VERY NICE
OF MRS. RICKET.
SHE HAD GEORGE IN HER CLASS.
MRS. RICKET WAS
VERY FOND OF GEORGE.
A LOT OF GEORGE'S TEACHERS
LIKED HER.
SO WHY'D SHE DROP OUT
OF COLLEGE?
TO MAKE ME MAD.
REALLY?
NO.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED.
I THINK SHE WOULD
HAVE GONE BACK...
YOU KNOW, EVENTUALLY.
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU SHOULD BRING
THAT BIOLOGY PROJECT
TO YOUR DAD'S.
ALL RIGHT? YOU CAN
FINISH IT THERE.
WHY CAN'T
I DO IT HERE?REGGIE.
HIS PLACE IS CHEESY.
THERE'S CARPETS
IN THE BATHROOM,
AND YOU CAN HEAR PEOPLE
MAKING SOUNDS
THROUGH THE WALL.
YOUR FATHER?NO, HIS FAT NEIGHBOR.
WHAT KIND OF SOUNDS?
BATHROOM SOUNDS.
UGH. THAT'S BAD.
AND I'LL NEVER
GET IT FINISHED THERE,
ANYWAY,
AND YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO'S GOOD AT
BUILDING STUFF.
HE WANTS TO SPEND
TIME WITH YOU.
HE EVEN ASKED
IF HE COULD GET YOU EARLY.
SO WHY DON'T YOU AND I
JUST GET STARTED ON IT,
AND IF WE DON'T
GET IT FINISHED
BY THE TIME
DAD GETS HERE...
YOU'LL FINISH IT.
REGGIE,
I CANNOT DO
ALL YOUR HOMEWORK
FOR YOU, OKAY?
YOU'LL NEVER LEARN ANYTHING.
YOU WANT ME
TO GET INTO COLLEGE,
DON'T YOU?
JUST GO
GET THE STUFF.
HOUSEKEEPING.
HEY, WHO STOLE
MY FUCKING CART?
ANYONE HERE?
HOUSEKEEPING.
OH, YES, COULD I GET
SOME FRESH TOWELS
IN THE BATH, PLEASE?
I JUST NEED
SOME FRESH TOWELS.
FOR ONE OR TWO?
UM, TWO, PLEASE.
HE LOVES FRESH TOWELS, SO...
THANK YOU, LATANYA.
SURE.
MY PLEASURE.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
WHAT EXQUISITE THINGS.
YOU THINK SO?YEAH.
I'D DO ANYTHING
FOR LOVELY THINGS
LIKE THIS.
WELL, I ACTUALLY HAVE...
WHICH ONE DO YOU THINK
I SHOULD WEAR?
IT'S NOT MY AREA
OF EXPERTISE.
BECAUSE I KNOW
THAT HE LIKES RED.
UM, I'VE SEEN HIS WIFE
WEAR A LOT OF RED.
THEN MAYBE
SOMETHING NOT RED.
RIGHT.
ISN'T THAT THE POINT?
DO SOMETHING DIFFERENT,
SOMETHING THAT MAYBE
HIS WIFE WOULDN'T DO?
TOO TRUE.
GO WITH THE PINK.
MEN LOVE PINK.
MAKES THEM FEEL LIKE
THE STRONG ONE.
THAT'S SO SMART.
I'VE GOT
A MILLION OF 'EM.
NICE HARD BED.
LOVE THAT.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
I WORRY ABOUT THE PINK,
BECAUSE I THINK
THAT WOULD LOOK
A BIT TOO DESPERATE?
NO, NO, NO, NOT DESPERATE.
DELICATE.
YEAH, I-- I'M...
I'M SORRY,
I'M JUST NERVOUS.
I, UM...
TODAY'S THE DAY.
I DECIDED I AM...
I'M JUST TIRED OF BEING
"TUESDAY AFTERNOON TESS."
I'M TIRED OF BEING
THE OTHER WOMAN.
I WANT TO BE
MRS. FRANK MANN.
I SHOULD LET YOU
GET READY.
OH, YES.
I'LL TAKE THOSE TOWELS.
THE PINK ONE
REALLY IS THE PRETTIEST.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
[WATER RUNNING]
[KNOCKING]
[MAID]
ROOM SERVICE.
[WOMAN]
I'LL BE OUT IN A MINUTE.
[GROWLING]SHH.
OOH... WHEN I CRASHED
THIS FUNERAL
A COUPLE WEEKS AGO,
THEY HAD THESE
SHRIMP PUFFY THINGS.
DO YOU HAVE ANY PRAWNS
WITH PUFFY PASTRY?
NO.
[MOCKING] "NO." GOD.
CAN WE GET CHINESE FOOD
AFTER THIS?
WHAT DO YOU THINK,
JACKET ON OR OFF?
OFF.
ACTUALLY, ON.
I THINK OFF, ACTUALLY.
ARE YOU FUCKING
WITH ME, MASON?
DON'T FUCK WITH ME
TODAY, MASON.
BLOODY HELL.
UH... OH.
HI.
I'M SORRY
FOR YOUR LOSS.
THANK YOU.
HI, GEORGE.HI.
UM, MASON, TRIP.
TRIP, MASON.
HI.
HELLO.
THE DEATH OF A LOVED ONE
IS NOT
A GLANCING BLOW,
BUT A DEEP
AND MEANINGFUL WOUND
THAT WE REGRET
MOST MISERABLY.
THANK YOU.
YOU ARE MOST HUMBLY
WELCOME, TRIP.
OOH!
WHEN DEATH'S DARK SHADOW
PASSES UPON US,
WE CANNOT HELP
BUT SEARCH FOR
THAT LIGHTNESS, TRIP,
BECAUSE IN THAT
FUCKING LIGHTNESS--
THERE'S AN OPEN BAR,
IF YOU'D LIKE.
THANKS, MAN. YEAH.
I LIKE HIM.
HE'S COOL.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU KEEP
CRASHING MY CLUB,
PEOPLE WILL START TO TALK.
WHAT WILL THEY SAY?
THAT YOU LIKE ME.
UH, TRIP?
OH.
LOOK, JUST GIVE ME
ONE SECOND, WILL YOU?
SO LET THEM TALK.
[KNOCKING]
COME IN.[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
YOU'RE LATE.
I HAVE A JOB, TESS.
I KNOW.
I KNOW ALL ABOUT
YOUR OBLIGATIONS.
DON'T START.I'M NOT.
AREN'T YOU GOING TO
SAY SOMETHING
ABOUT MY OUTFIT?
[MAN] I TOLD YOU
NOT TO CALL MY HOUSE.
WELL, YOU WOULDN'T
TAKE MY CALLS AT WORK.
WHAT'S A GIRL TO THINK?
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE
CALLED MY HOUSE, TESS.
DON'T BE MAD,
SWEETHEART.
I AM NOT
YOUR SWEETHEART.
IT'S THE ONE THING
I TOLD YOU NOT TO DO.
THE ONE THING.
YOU CAN'T MAKE ME
WAIT FOREVER.
I'M NOT JUST
GOING TO DISAPPEAR, FRANK.
YES, YOU ARE.
[TESS SCREAMING]
[TESS CHOKING]
FUCK ME, YOU WERE UGLY.
AND YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU WERE REALLY MEAN.
NO WONDER YOU PEOPLE
DRINK SO MUCH.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
OH, IT'S OKAY.
DO YOU TALK TO DEAD PEOPLE?
WHAT?
YOUR FRIEND,
HE WAS, UH, TALKING
TO A DEAD WOMAN.
WHO DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE TALKING TO, BUSTER?
SO, UH, MASON,
WHY DID YOU BRING HIM?
I GUESS I WASN'T SURE.
ABOUT?YOU.
HE'S KIND OF
MY INSURANCE POLICY.
WHAT IF I TOLD YOU
THAT WHEN WE WERE
BURYING MY FATHER,
I FLASHED ON KISSING YOU?
AND WHEN I WAS
DELIVERING HIS EULOGY,
I FLASHED
ON KISSING YOU.
I KNOW IT'S NOT
NORMAL, BUT...
I THINK...
WHEN SOMEONE
YOU REALLY LOVE DIES,
YOU GET A PASS ON NORMAL.
TRIP!
COME SAY HELLO
TO THE FERGUSONS.
WHO IS THAT?
THAT'S MY SISTER, ASHLEY.
LOOK, I'LL BE BACK,
ALL RIGHT?
GEORGE, I THINK
IT'S A REALLY GOOD TIME
FOR US TO
GET OUT OF HERE.
BECAUSE I HAVE TO
DO MY REAP?
NO, BECAUSE I JUST STOLE
A REALLY BIG DIAMOND
OFF A REALLY LITTLE
LAP DOG.
ONE OF THOSE
ANNOYING POODLES?
NO, SHIH TZU, I THINK.
IF I HAD COFFEE AFTER LUNCH,
I'D BE UP ALL NIGHT.
I'M UP ANYWAY.
THANKS, KIFFANY.YOU'RE WELCOME.
NEIGHBORS?
NIGHTMARES.
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER PLAYING]
I CAN REMEMBER
WHEN COFFEE WAS A NICKEL.
TEN CENTS AND A CRYING BABY,
KEEP YOU UP ALL NIGHT.
I'M GOING AWAY
FOR A COUPLE DAYS.
I NEED YOU TO
COVER FOR ME.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
AWAY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M DOING
A LITTLE RESEARCH.
ON WHAT?ROXY.
YOU ASK ME
FOR A FUCKING FAVOR
AND THEN YOU ZIP UP?
I DON'T THINK SO.
I SENT SOMETHING TO SOMEONE
A LONG TIME AGO
AND IT DIDN'T
GET TO THAT SOMEONE,
AND I'M TRYING TO DO
A LITTLE FOLLOW-UP.
WERE YOU DEAD
WHEN YOU SENT IT?
ROXY.WERE YOU DEAD
YES.
REALLY?
IS THIS SOMEONE
DEAD OR ALIVE TODAY?
DEAD, ROXY.
COFFEE WAS A NICKEL.
NOW LEAVE ME ALONE
AND JUST LET ME
ENJOY MY PIE IN PEACE.
FINE.FINE.
DO THE POST-ITS FOR ME?
I APPRECIATE IT.
[RADIO]  WE HAVE A 187
AT THE MILLSTONE HOTEL.
I'LL COVER FOR YOU.
WHAT DO YOU
WANT TO DO? MOVIE?
THERE'S NOTHING GOOD OUT.
WANT TO GO
TO THE DELANEY HOUSE
FOR SOME FRIED CLAMS?
I'D RATHER JUST WATCH T.V.
OKAY.
SO WE'RE EATING IN.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE?
WHATEVER THE DELIVERY GUY
BRINGS TO MY DOOR.
DAD...
DID YOU AND CHARLOTTE
BREAK UP?
WELL, WHY WOULD YOU
ASK THAT?
SHE COOKED.
WE DID.
WE BROKE UP.
DID SHE DUMP YOU?
REGGIE, PEOPLE DON'T
DUMP ONE ANOTHER
IN A MATURE RELATIONSHIP.
SO SHE DUMPED YOU?
YES.
CHARLOTTE REALLY
LIKED YOU, THOUGH.
SHE TOLD ME SHE WAS REALLY
GOING TO MISS YOU.
I WASN'T CRAZY ABOUT HER.
SO YOU AND YOUR MOM
HAVE SOMETHING IN COMMON.
SO... NO HOMEWORK?
MOM'S DOING IT.
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE YOU CAN
DO YOUR HOMEWORK
OVER HERE, REG.
I CAN HELP YOU.
I AM A TEACHER.
YOU COULDN'T HANDLE IT.
IT'S SCIENCE.
ENGLISH TEACHERS
CAN DO SCIENCE.
MOM'S DOING IT.
REGGIE, I REALLY DON'T WANT
YOUR MOM DOING
YOUR HOMEWORK WITHOUT YOU.
IT'S, WELL, IT'S CHEATING,
AND YOU KNOW
HOW I FEEL ABOUT THAT.
OKAY.
SO WHAT'S THE ASSIGNMENT?
WE HAVE TO MAKE A MODEL
OF THE HEART.
OUT OF WHAT?ANYTHING.
COOL.
LOVELY.
DO YOU THINK
THEY TAKE REQUESTS?
I'LL ASK THEM.
"FREEBIRD!"
"FREEBIRD--"
YEAH, FREE, FREEBIRD!
CAN I BUY YOU
A DRINK?
IT'S A PRIVATE CLUB.
YOU DON'T
BUY PEOPLE DRINKS.
WHOO.
BITCHY HEIRESS.
YOU'RE JUST MY TYPE.
I LOVE IT.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?MASON. WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
DON'T TELL ME.
OOH, I LOVE THIS GAME.
WHITNEY?
PARKER?
WHITNEY?YOU ALREADY SAID THAT.
PARKER?IT'S ASHLEY.
FUCKING BOLLOCKS.
BULLSHIT. BULLBAGS.
I KNEW IT.
WHY ARE YOU HERE?HESBURGH FUNERAL.
I'M ASHLEY HESBURGH.
AND I'M VERY SORRY.
WHY ARE  YOUHERE?
I'M WITH HER.
YEAH?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW
HER EITHER. WHO IS SHE?
SHE'S TRIP'S GIRLFRIEND.
REALLY?YES.
AND YET I'VE NEVER
SEEN HER BEFORE.
BET THERE'S A LOT
YOU HAVEN'T SEEN
BEFORE, WHITNEY.
SURE.
BUY ME A DRINK.
REALLY?MM.
REALLY?
MM.
WHOO. ANOTHER DRINK
FOR THIS YOUNG LADY, PLEASE,
AND PUT IT ON MY TAB.
FUCKING BOLLOCKS.
[YAPS]WHY ARE WE HERE AGAIN?
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT
TO HAVE TO TALK
TO ANYBODY.
EXCEPT YOU.
MY SISTER AND I
STARTED DOING THIS
WHEN WE WERE KIDS.
YOU KNOW,
ANYTHING TO GET AWAY.
IT'S SWEET THAT YOU TALK
TO YOUR SISTER.
I TOTALLY IGNORED MINE.
YOU DON'T
TALK TO HER ANYMORE?
WHY?
WELL, YOU JUST--
YOU USED THE PAST TENSE.
WELL, HOW ABOUT WE NOT
TALK ABOUT OUR FAMILIES?
DEAL.
WE DON'T HAVE TO TALK
ABOUT ANYTHING.
THIS IS SO NOT RIGHT.
I HAVE A DEAD PERSON
TO DEAL WITH,
HE'S GOT A DEAD PERSON
BUT FOR JUST A MOMENT,
THIS WAS A NICE
LITTLE HIDING PLACE.
TRIP.
BUSTED.
I HAVEN'T BEEN INTRODUCED
TO YOUR FRIEND.
I'M SORRY.
UM, GEORGE,
THIS IS
MY SISTER, ASHLEY.
ASHLEY, THIS IS GEORGE.
HI.
I'M SO SORRY
FOR YOUR LOSS.
THANK YOU.
MAYBE WE SHOULD...
YEAH, YEAH, THAT WOULD BE...
LADIES FIRST.
THANK YOU.
OH! FOUND
MY CONTACT LENS.
THANK GOD.
CAN'T SEE A THING.
SO HOW LONG
HAVE YOU TWO LOVEBIRDS
BEEN TOGETHER?
WHAT'S UP, ASHLEY?
WELL, I'M JUST
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHY YOU'RE AT
OUR FATHER'S
MEMORIAL SERVICE
DOING THE HIDEOUT ROUTINE
WITH SOME GIRL
I'VE NEVER SEEN BEFORE.
ASHLEY, YOU'RE BEING
IMPOLITE.
ACTUALLY, TRIP,
YOU'RE BEING IMPOLITE.
YOU HAVE SPENT
ALL OF THREE SECONDS
TALKING TO DAD'S FRIENDS.
I SHOULD PROBABLY JUST GO.
DON'T BE SILLY.
SO, HOW LONG HAVE YOU TWO
BEEN AN ITEM?
THAT'S ENOUGH,
ALL RIGHT?
SEE, BECAUSE, UH-- OH!
MASON HERE SAYS THAT
GEORGE IS YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
MASON.
YEAH,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
ACTUALLY, SHE IS.
I AM?
WELL, THAT'S NICE.
WELCOME TO THE FAMILY.
GEORGE...
I DIDN'T CATCH A LAST NAME.
WHAT IS YOUR LAST NAME?
NO. DON'T.
LASS.
OKAY, SO, SHE'S
YOUR GIRLFRIEND,
AND YOU DON'T EVEN
KNOW HER LAST NAME?
GEORGE, WE HAVE
TO GO NOW.
MAYBE I'M JUST A SPOILSPORT,
BUT DAD IS DEAD,
AND THIS ISN'T FUNNY ANYMORE,
AND YOU, LITTLE BROTHER,
NEED TO GROW THE FUCK UP.
I'VE GOT TO GO.
THAT'S COOL...
UH, SO DO I.
I'M SORRY.
DON'T BE.
JUST GO DO
YOUR THING.
YOU SHOULDN'T NOT HAVE
TOLD HIM YOUR LAST NAME.
GEORGE LASS IS DEAD.
I GOT TO GO REAP SOMEBODY.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I WAS THINKING.
WHO AM I KIDDING?
THIS ISN'T ME.
I HAD TO GET OUT OF THERE.
THIS PLACE WAS MEMBERS ONLY,
AND I WAS, AS MASON SAID,
NOT REALLY ELIGIBLE.
WHAT'S UP?
THE OLDEST STORY
IN THE WORLD.
GUY'S TRYING
TO UNLOAD HIS MISTRESS
WHO GOT TO BE
A PAIN IN THE ASS.
DID HE LEAVE ANY PRINTS?
DIDN'T HAVE TO.
WE FOUND HIS NAME
WRITTEN ON A HOTEL PAD
BY THE PHONE.
LIKE SHE WAS
SPEAKING TO US
FROM THE DEAD.
PRETTY HANDWRITING.
GUESS HE WON'T BE
HURTING ANYBODY ANYMORE.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
WE'VE GOT THINGS
PRETTY MUCH WRAPPED UP
AROUND HERE.
NOT QUITE EVERYTHING.
I GOT YOU, SWEETHEART.
YOU'RE OKAY.
COME WITH ME.
I HAD IT ALL WRONG.
YOU DON'T GO TO A FUNERAL
TO MEET A GUY.
YOU GO TO A WEDDING...
WHERE THERE'S LOTS OF GUYS.
ALL GUYS.
ALL THE TIME.
SO, ARE YOU
WITH THE GROOM
OR THE GROOM?
HUH?
I'M JUST GLAD
THAT KYLE AND JEFFREY
ARE FINALLY
MAKING THIS OFFICIAL.
NO SURPRISES
ON THAT WEDDING NIGHT,
YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M SAYING.
I'M GORDON.
GORDON MAYNARD.
I KNOW.
I'M NOT FUNNY,
BUT I WAS JUST
TRYING TO MEET SOMEONE,
AND YOU SEEM NICE.
I'M KIND OF HERE
WITH SOMEBODY.
OKAY.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
HE DIDN'T SEEM LIKE
YOUR TYPE ANYWAY, AT ALL.
OH, YEAH. I KNOW.
GORGEOUS GUYS,
THEY'RE JUST
SO HIGH-MAINTENANCE.
WELL...
YOU'RE GORGEOUS.
YOU'RE A GIRL.
BUT THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL THROW IT.
WE'RE NOT
THROWING IT.
JUST THROW
THE FUCKING THING.
IT'S A PHOTO-OP.
FINE.
HERE WE GO!
HONEY?
OVER THE SHOULDER.
RIGHT.
I'VE GOT TO CATCH
THE BOUQUET.
WELL, GO, GIVE IT
YOUR BEST SHOT.
MM. WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
I, UH, MADE
THE WEDDING CAKE.
ONE...
TWO...
THREE!
HI, GAIL. IT'S JOY.
I'M REALLY SORRY,
BUT I'M NOT GOING TO BE ABLE
TO MAKE IT TONIGHT.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I REALLY WANT TO START
JOINING YOU GUYS
ON THESE GIRLS'
NIGHTS OUT, I DO,
BUT I'M JUST
NOT FEELING WELL.
YEAH.
WELL, WE'LL DO IT
ANOTHER TIME, RIGHT?
I PROMISE.
OKAY. YEAH, THANKS, GAIL.
SOMETIMES, YOU JUST HAVE TO
LOSE YOURSELF IN YOUR WORK.
LOSING YOURSELF IN YOUR WORK
COULD BE A GOOD THING.
BUT JUST BEING A LOSER...
NOT SUCH A GOOD THING.
GORDON?
ARE YOU OKAY?
HE DOESN'T LOOK GOOD.
HE NEVER
LOOKED GOOD.
HE'S NOT MOVING.
CALL AN AMBULANCE.
OKAY.
WHAT HAPPENED?
DID I EVEN GET IT?
YOU GOT IT.
GREAT.
THEY'RE ALL HOOKING UP
WITH EACH OTHER
OVER MY DEATH,
AND I'M ALONE.
YOU'RE NOT ALONE.
I DIED
WITHOUT A BOYFRIEND.
I DON'T SUPPOSE
THERE'S ANY CHANCE
OF GETTING ONE
ON THE OTHER SIDE?
THAT'S A GOOD
QUESTION, GORDON.
WHAT'S THE ANSWER?
I'M STILL TRYING
TO FIGURE IT OUT MYSELF.
BUT FOR NOW,
I'M HERE FOR YOU.
I KNOW I'M NOT
EXACTLY YOUR TYPE,
BUT...
I CAN BE BITCHY.
BITCHY'S COOL.
AND HEY, YOU SNAGGED
THE BOUQUET.
TRUE.
GORDON, I THINK
YOU'RE READY.
NOBODY SHOULD
HAVE TO FACE DEATH ALONE.
[VIOLIN PLAYING]
NOT IN THE MOOD.
YOU ARE SOME KIND
OF FUCK-UP.
THIS IS
SOME MASON SHIT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
YOU LEAVE THE SOUL,
AND YOU FINGER THE MURDERER.
I DID NOTHING OF THE KIND.
YOU LEFT THE MAN'S NAME!
NO, I DIDN'T.
I KNOW YOUR
HANDWRITING, DAISY.
YOUR SILLY
LITTLE CURLICUES.
WHAT THE FUCK
DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
I JUST DIDN'T WANT HIM
TO GET AWAY WITH IT, OKAY?
THAT'S NOT YOUR JOB.
YOUR JOB IS TO HANDLE
THAT WOMAN'S SOUL.
EVERYBODY HAS SOMETHING
THEY DON'T DEAL WITH, ROXY.
RUBE DOESN'T DO KIDS.
I DON'T DO THOSE.
THOSE WHAT?WOMEN WHO END UP THAT WAY.
DEFENSELESS,
WITH A MAN COMING AT THEM.
I CAN'T WATCH IT.
THAT NEVER
HAPPENED TO YOU.
I DIDN'T SAY
IT HAPPENED TO ME.
THEN WHAT ARE YOU
FEELING SO GUILTY ABOUT?
I JUST FEEL GUILTY.
CAN'T A GIRL FEEL GUILTY?
MAYBE YOU NEED
TO GO BACK TO CHURCH.
MAYBE WE'RE DONE
TALKING ABOUT THIS.
DOESN'T THAT
FUCK WITH YOUR SLEEP?
I'M UP ANYWAY.
CAN I GET YOU
ANYTHING?
COFFEE.
THE COOL THING
ABOUT BEING A REAPER
WAS YOU KIND OF HAD
A SECOND CHANCE
TO MAKE THINGS RIGHT.
ANOTHER WHACK
AT THE PINATA.
SEE IF I COULD GET THE THING
TO BREAK OPEN...
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE THE PARTY
WAS ALREADY OVER.
THIS IS GOING TO BE
BEAUTIFUL, SWEETIE.
MAYBE THE LIGHTS WENT OUT
AND I JUST COULDN'T SEE IT.
I DON'T KNOW.
BEING DEAD, I COULD HANDLE.
BEING TOTALLY ALONE
WAS SOMETHING ELSE.
BEING ALONE WAS TOO MUCH.
OR IT WAS
JUST TOO MUCH TODAY.
OH, MY GOD!
HI.
WHO TOLD YOU WHERE--YOUR FRIEND, MASON.
[SIGHS]
MASON...
MASON, MASON.
LOOK, AT THE RISK
OF SOUNDING
COMPLETELY STALKERISH,
I FOUND SOMETHING
OF YOURS,
AND I JUST THOUGHT
I SHOULD
GIVE IT BACK TO YOU.
CHECK IT OUT...
DEAD CINDERELLA.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE
COME TODAY.
NO. NO, NO, NO.
OF COURSE, YOU SHOULD HAVE.
IT WAS JUST...
IT WAS BAD TIMING.
I'M SORRY.
ABOUT YOUR DAD.
YOU KNOW, THEY'RE ALL
AT THE HOUSE RIGHT NOW.
I JUST--
I COULDN'T GET SLOBBERED ON
BY ANOTHER OLD LADY
TELLING ME
WHAT A GREAT MAN
MY DAD WAS.
DOES THAT
MAKE ME SHALLOW?I'M INTO SHALLOW.
SHALLOW'S THE NEW DEEP,
HAVEN'T YOU HEARD?
I JUST COULDN'T LISTEN
TO ONE MORE PERSON
TELLING ME, YOU KNOW,
"DO YOU KNOW HOW PROUD
YOUR FATHER WAS?"
DO YOU WANT TO KISS ME?
PLEASE.
I MEAN, I KNOW
THAT HE WAS PROUD OF ME.
HE TOLD ME
HE WAS PROUD OF ME.
I DON'T KNOW WHY
I HAVE TO LISTEN TO IT
FROM SO MANY OTHER PEOPLE.
DO YOU WANT TO
GO BACK THERE...
OR DO YOU WANT
TO BE HERE?
I WANT TO BE HERE.
I WASN'T READY FOR MY DEATH
AND IT CAME ANYWAY.
AND I WASN'T READY FOR THIS,
BUT HERE IT CAME ANYWAY.
LIKE SOMETHING, I DON'T KNOW,
FALLING ON ME...
OUT OF THE SKY.
IT WAS PRETTY NICE
TO HAVE SOMEONE
TRACK ME DOWN FOR ONCE,
TO THINK SOMEONE CARED
THAT I WAS GONE.
WHAT IS THIS VISION
OF LOVELINESS
I SEE BEFORE ME?
NYMPH? ANGEL?
NOT TONIGHT.
YOU'RE WEARING
GOLF SHOES.
SHUT UP. NO WAY.
IS THAT
WHAT THEY ARE?
BLOODY HELL.
THEY'RE VERY SMART,
AREN'T THEY?
LOVELY.
I HAVE HAD
THE MOST INCREDIBLE DAY.
IT'S BEEN BOOZE,
IT'S BEEN FOOD,
IT'S BEEN PETTY LARCENY.
IT'S BEEN ABSOLUTELY
FUCKING FANTASTIC.
WISH YOU WOULD HAVE
BEEN THERE. I MISSED YOU.
THAT'S NICE.
KIFFANY, CAN I INTEREST YOU
IN A VERY, VERY GOOD DEAL
ON A VERY NICE GOLD WATCH?
HOW ABOUT A NICE,
FASHIONABLE CLUTCH BAG?
NO.
YOU CAN'T WEAR
GOLF SHOES IN HERE.
WHY NOT?
FUCKS UP THE FLOORS.
OKAY.
YOU WANT
SOME MORE COFFEE, HON?
I'M DONE. THANKS.
SHE HATES ME.
SHE'S HAD A LONG DAY,
AND SO HAVE I.
WHAT'S WRONG?
NOTHING.
REALLY?
I'VE GOT SOMETHING FOR YOU
AS WELL, DAISY ADAIR.
TAH-DAH!
WOW. A GIRL'S
BEST FRIEND.
STOLEN FROM
MAN'S BEST FRIEND.
A DOG?A REALLY WEALTHY DOG.
I THOUGHT IT MIGHT BE
TOO SMALL
TO GO AROUND YOUR NECK,
SO YOU CAN WEAR IT
AS A BRACELET.
HERE. LET ME HELP YOU.
I LOVE IT.
I LOVE YOU LOVING IT...
LOVE.
DID I EVER TELL YOU
I HAD A SISTER?
NO.
WHY DON'T YOU
TELL ME ALL ABOUT IT?
KIFFANY, PLEASE
COULD I HAVE A COFFEE?
ONE COFFEE.
SO, THANKS FOR
SLEEPING OVER, REG.
SURE.
DID YOU HAVE FUN?
I'M SORRY
ABOUT CHARLOTTE.
YOU'LL GET OVER
GETTING DUMPED.
MOM DID.
SO I'LL SEE YOU ON FRIDAY.
HEY, UH...
COME ON OVER EARLY
IF YOU LIKE.
OKAY.
THANKS FOR HELPING ME
WITH MY PROJECT.
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU, SWEETIE.
HI, HONEY. WHAT IS THAT?
DAD HELPED ME
WITH MY HEART ASSIGNMENT.
[J.D. BARKING]
HEY, J.D., BUDDY!
COME HERE.
COME ON! UP. YES!
REGGIE!
I WAS UP ALL NIGHT
WORKING ON THAT.
HE WANTED TO.[SIGHS]
SO, YOUR FATHER
WORKING ON
A SCIENCE PROJECT...
WELL, I'M SURE
IT'S VERY ACCURATE.
IT'S A POEM.
HE SAID FOR YOU TO READ IT.
HE SAID THE END'S
THE BEST PART.
"SINCE SWEETS AND BEAUTIES
DO THEMSELVES FORSAKE
"AND DIE AS FAST
"AS THEY SEE OTHERS GROW
"AND NOTHING
'GAINST TIME'S SCYTHE
"CAN MAKE DEFENSE
"SAVE BREED
"TO BRAVE HIM
WHEN HE TAKES THEE HENCE."
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
SHAKESPEARE.
IT MEANS THAT...
IT MEANS
YOU SHOULD HAVE KIDS,
BECAUSE THEN YOU'RE
NEVER ALONE.
IS DAD TRYING TO GET BACK
TOGETHER WITH YOU?
NO, SWEETIE. NO.
HE DID IT FOR YOU.
IT'S ABOUT YOU.
IS THAT
WHAT YOU MADE?
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT HAPPENED?
[SIGHS]
J.D. ATE IT.
REGGIE, YOU HAVE
TO LEAVE FOR SCHOOL
IN 10 MINUTES.
I HAVEN'T EVEN
HAD MY COFFEE YET.
I LIKE IT.
OKAY, I DIDN'T HATE IT,
BUT IT WAS WEIRD.
I HADN'T EXACTLY
BEEN CLOSE TO ANYONE.
IN A WHILE.
OKAY, EVER...
AND SUDDENLY,
SOMEONE HAD GOTTEN
VERY CLOSE.
AND THEN THEY DISAPPEARED.
OH, WHAT THE FUCK?
HI.HI.
COFFEE?
OF COURSE.
THOUGHT
I'D LET YOU SLEEP.
THANKS.
SO...
SO.
I THINK I KNOW
WHY PEOPLE USE
THAT STUPID PHRASE
"DOING IT."
BECAUSE IT'S SO FUCKING HARD
TO TALK ABOUT.
I HOPE YOU KNOW THAT
I WASN'T, YOU KNOW,
PLANNING THAT.
OH, NO. ME EITHER.
I WAS HOPING FOR IT.
YEAH, ME TOO.
TOTALLY.
THERE WE WERE,
IN ONE OF THOSE BUBBLES
YOU BLOW AS A KID--
KIND OF ROUND AND PERFECT
AND JUST A LITTLE STRANGE,
FLOATING IN THE AIR...
SO THIS WAS FUN.
AND THERE IT GOES--
POP.
YEAH. IT WAS... FUN.
SO I'LL... I'LL CALL YOU.
IF YOU WANT. I JUST...
I MEAN, I KNOW YOU HAVE
A LOT OF THINGS TO DO,
BUT IF YOU WANT,
YOU CAN CALL.
OKAY.
SO YOU'RE COOL?
OH, YEAH. TOTALLY COOL.
OH, MY FUCKING GOD,
THAT'S HOT.
SO MAYBE I WAS A VIRGIN
WHEN IT CAME
TO THE SEX THING...
SO I'LL SEE YOU.
BUT HE WAS A VIRGIN, TOO--
FIRST BIG DEATH.
AND YOU NEVER REALLY KNOW
WHAT DEATH WILL MAKE YOU DO...
HOW YOU TRY TO DEFY IT...
TO REACH PAST
WHAT'S POSSIBLE.
HOW YOU STRUGGLE
TO FIT THE PIECES TOGETHER
EVEN THOUGH
THEY'RE WAY TOO BROKEN
TO BOTHER.
I DON'T KNOW.
"SINCE SWEETS AND BEAUTIES
DO THEMSELVES FORSAKE
"AND DIE AS FAST
AS THEY SEE OTHERS GROW
"AND NOTHING
'GAINST TIME'S SCYTHE
CAN MAKE DEFENCE..."
I DO KNOW THAT,
THAT MORNING,
I FELT LIKE MY HEART,
OR WHATEVER IT WAS
THAT WAS IN MY CHEST,
WAS STILL GOING.
NICE JOB, MILLIE.
YOU BROUGHT HER
BACK TO LIFE.
THANKS.