[GEORGE]:  DEEP DOWN,
WE ALL WANT TO KNOW
IF WE'RE LOVED.
IT'S THE FUNDAMENTAL QUESTION,
BUT WHEN I WAS A KID,
THE QUESTION
WAS EVEN MORE BASIC.
DOES ANYONE EVEN LIKE ME?
I'M SURE THERE'S
ALL KINDS OF THEORIES
ON HOW TO HELP GIRLS
GET OVER THEIR INSECURITIES
AND SELF DOUBTS,
BUT IT TAKES
A PRETTY TWISTED MIND
TO THINK THAT "SWIM DAY"
IS THE ANSWER.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
THANKS A LOT, MOM.
COME ON.
HEY.
WHY DON'T YOU GO SAY HI
TO YOUR FRIENDS, SWEETIE?
LOOK, GEORGIA,
IT'S NOT GOING TO KILL YOU
TO MAKE A FRIEND.
IT MIGHT.
FINE. THEN LET'S GO HOME.
I'M NOT WEARING THE FLOATIES.
BUT YOU'RE A REALLY BAD...
YOU'RE NOT A STRONG
SWIMMER, GEORGE.
I'D RATHER DROWN.
[GEORGE]:  WHEN I WAS 10,
I LEARNED ONE OF LIFE'S
MOST VALUABLE LESSONS.
NO MATTER HOW UNCOOL
YOU THINK YOU ARE,
THERE'S SOMEONE EVEN LESS COOL
JUST A POOL'S LENGTH AWAY...
HI, GEORGE.
[GEORGE]:  AND THAT SOMEONE
WAS BETH ANNE MILLER.
[GIGGLING]
OH, SHIT.
RECENTLY,
I'VE BEEN THINKING A LOT
ABOUT CROSSING OVER,
BUT WHEN YOU'RE ALIVE,
CROSSING OVER IS EVEN HARDER.
MUCH HARDER.
SO...
DO YOU WANT TO GO SHOPPING
THIS AFTERNOON?
WHAT FOR?A NEW SWEATER.
YEAH, THAT ONE'S
PRETTY TRAGIC.
I MEANT FOR YOU, REGGIE.
I HAVE HOMEWORK.
YOU KNOW,
OTHER GIRLS YOUR AGE
LIKE TO GO TO THE MALL.
IT'S COOL.
STEALING LIP GLOSS
AND SMOKING BEHIND
THE FOOD COURT'S COOL?
FINE, REGGIE.
STAY HERE AND WORK
ON THAT ATTITUDE.
IT'S PRETTY.
I'LL CALL THE SITTER.
NO.
I'LL GO.
WHAT IS SO TRAGIC
ABOUT THIS SWEATER?
GO.
[SPLASHING]
THIS IS THE CRUCIAL STEP.
THE UNSUSPECTING PATRON
PERUSES HIS MENU
AND SELECTS THE OPTIONS.
KIFFANY SWINGS BY.
SHE PRETENDS
NOT TO NOTICE HIM,
THEREBY MAKING HIM FEEL
DESPERATELY FOOLISH.
CASTRATED.
LIMP AND WORTHLESS.
A RIGHT TURD.
NOW SHE OWNS HIM.
HE'S UNDER HER POWER.
OBSERVE.
ABSOLUTELY BRUTAL.
IF PEOPLE THINK
YOU DON'T LIKE THEM,
THEY WANT IT EVEN MORE.
IT'S PATHETIC,
REALLY, ISN'T IT?YEAH.
YEAH.
HEY, CAPTAIN ASSHOLE.
YEAH?
THIS VIEW IS RUINING
A PERFECTLY GOOD BREAKFAST.
I'LL HAVE YOU KNOW,
MEN HAVE DIED
FOR THAT VIEW.
OKAY, SO THAT WAS
TODAY'S LESSON
FROM THE WAFFLE HAUS.
WITHHOLD THE LOVE,
AND YOU GAIN THE POWER.
HEY, GEORGE,
YOU WANT TO COME
OUT OF THE POOL?
NO.
I LIKE IT HERE.
WILL RESURFACE FOR FOOD.
YOU...
YOU.POOLS?
I HATE POOLS. I HATE WATER.
I HATE DROWNING.
I HATE ANYTHING
THAT MAKES SOMEBODY BLUE.
WHAT ABOUT SINGING THE BLUES?
THAT'S ALWAYS NICE.
DROWNING IS A REALLY,
REALLY HORRIBLE WAY TO DIE.
♪ I AM BLUE
♪ I'M BLUE
BECAUSE OF YOU ♪
YOU GOT
THE BLOND-HAIRED,
BLUE-EYED BLUES
AGAIN, DAISY?
YES.
HIT ME, RUBE.NICE TO SEE YOU, ROXY.
WHY DON'T YOU
STAY A WHILE?
I WOULD,
BUT I DON'T WANT TO.
NOW, ROXY HERE
IS A CLASSIC WITHHOLDER.
SHE INSPIRES FEAR
THROUGH RESTRAINT.
I INSPIRE FEAR
THROUGH MY
NINE MILLIMETER
AND MY
PENETRATING GAZE.
IS THAT A PEPPER SPRAY
ON YOUR FANCY
UTILITY BELT, ROXY?
IT IS, MASON.
YOU WANT TO PLAY
WITH IT?
YES.
YOU ARE SO INTO PAIN.
MM-HMM.
[SPUTTERS]
ACTUALLY,
THAT ISN'T PEPPER.
IT'S CHEMICALS.
YEAH, RIGHT, ROXY.
WHATEVER YOU SAY.
TOXIC CHEMICALS.
[MUFFLED SCREAM]
IF YOU WANT TO
BEAT HIM SENSELESS,
NOBODY'S GOING
TO WORRY ABOUT IT,
IF YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M SAYING.
THAT BETTER
NOT BE MY TIP.
NO.
I'LL PUT UP WITH A LOT,
BUT I WILL NOT PUT UP
WITH THAT.
I'M SORRY, KIFFANY.
IT'S JUST THAT MY EGGS
WEREN'T EXACTLY LOVELY
THIS MORNING.
MAYBE YOU SHOULDN'T
HAVE MACED THEM.
THANKS, KIFFANY.
SEE, RUBE?
YOU HAVE THE POWER
IN THAT RELATIONSHIP.
SHE LOVES YOU.
SHE HATES ME.
I TIP TWO DOLLARS
ON A SEVEN-DOLLAR
BREAKFAST.
IT'S NOT BRAIN SURGERY.
THIS IS IN, LIKE,
FIVE MINUTES.
WELL, MAYBE YOU SHOULD,
LIKE, GET A MOVE ON.
YOU DO THAT,
YOU KNOW.
YOU WITHHOLD THE LOVE.
YEAH.
HOW CAN I WITHHOLD
THAT WHICH I
DO NOT POSSESS?
EAT YOUR BREAKFAST.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[GEORGE]:  MOST GIRLS
ARE LATE FOR WORK
BECAUSE THEY OVERSLEPT
OR THEY MISSED THEIR BUS.
MOST GIRLS DIDN'T HAVE
TO SPEND THEIR MORNINGS
WATCHING A GUY TRY TO REPAIR
HIS OWN LAWN MOWER.
[MOTOR GRINDING]
SUCCESSFULLY, I MIGHT ADD.
[MOTOR ROARS]
[SCREAMS]
SLURPEE.
THE GREAT THING ABOUT WORK
IS NO MATTER HOW FUCKED UP
YOUR PERSONAL LIFE IS,
YOUR PROFESSIONAL LIFE
CAN MAKE IT SEEM NORMAL.
HOLY SHIT. SORRY.
ARE YOU OKAY?
I THINK
I'M GOING TO HURL.
NO, PLEASE, DON'T.
BLOWS TO THE HEAD
ALWAYS MAKE ME THROW UP.
HOW MANY BLOWS TO THE HEAD
HAVE YOU TAKEN?
A LOT. IN HIGH SCHOOL.
OH, GOD. BLOOD.
HERE COMES THE  McMUFFIN.
IT'S A SLURPEE.
OH. OKAY.
I'M BETTER.
THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
WHO ARE YOU?ETHAN. INFORMATION SYSTEMS.
COMPUTER GEEKS,
FIFTH FLOOR.
YOU'VE ACCESSED MY FILES?
DELORES SAID
IT WAS OKAY.
I'VE BEEN BEATEN UP A LOT,
AND I'M A BLEEDER,
AND THAT DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE A SLURPEE.
IT'S A CHERRY
SLURPEE, ETHAN.
CHILL THE FUCK OUT.
OKAY, FINE. MY BAD.
I'M SO SORRY,
MILLIE.
I... WHOA.
SLURPEE.
I WANTED TO BE HERE
TO INTRODUCE YOU
TO ETHAN,
BUT ANDY IN PERSONNEL
HAS CARPAL TUNNEL
IN BOTH HANDS--
CAN'T EVEN PEE
BY HIMSELF--
ANYHOO,
ETHAN IS ONE
OF THE TOP DOGS IN I.S.
HE'S HERE TO HELP US
WITH THE NAZI ISSUE.
WHAT NAZI ISSUE?
WHO'S A NAZI?
ACTUALLY, YOU ARE,
BUT SEE,
THERE'S A FUNNY
REASON BEHIND THAT.
I MEAN, IF YOU FIND
THAT SORT OF THING FUNNY.
ETHAN IS A GENIUS.
HUMOR HIM.
SEE, THERE'S THIS GROUP
IN OREGON,
AND SOMEONE PUT A BOT
ON YOUR HARD DRIVE,
AND THEY'VE BEEN
USING YOUR E-MAIL
TO MAIL OUT THEIR,
UM...
LITERATURE.
TO WHO?
"TO WHOM,"
BUT THAT'S COOL.
EVERYBODY MAKES
THAT MISTAKE.
ANSWER THE QUESTION.
EVERYONE IN THIS OFFICE,
AND, LIKE, A MILLION PEOPLE
ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
SO EVERYONE THINKS I'M A...
YEP, MAYBE.
PROBABLY.
DEFINITELY.
UH...
EXCUSE ME, EVERYONE.
COULD I HAVE EVERYONE'S
ATTENTION, PLEASE?
[MAN]: WHOO!
TAKE IT OFF!
OH, SHUT UP, YOU IDIOT.
I AM NOT A NAZI.
UH...
THERE WAS A, UH...
WHAT WAS IT?
ETHAN!A BOT.
A BOT IN MY
COMPUTER,
AND A...
SLURPEE.
THANK YOU
FOR YOUR TIME.
OH, MY GOD. THIS SUCKS.
OH, MILLIE,
THIS IS NOTHING.
YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN
THE TATTOOS I'VE HAD
TO HAVE REMOVED.
I'M NOT A NAZI.
YOU KNOW, IN HERE,
I DON'T THINK
ANY OF US REALLY IS.
SO, FOR WHAT
IT'S WORTH,
I NEVER THOUGHT
YOU WERE A NAZI.
SHH.
SO, UM...
I GUESS I SHOULDN'T
HAVE BEEN IN YOUR SEAT.
THAT'S LIKE
A HUGE CORPORATE FAUX PAS,
A BREACH OF PROTOCOL
OR SOMETHING.
I'M NOT SOMEONE IMPORTANT.
TELL THAT
TO THE FIFTH FLOOR.
THE OTHER GUYS
WERE INSANELY JEALOUS
I GOT TO WORK
ON YOUR COMPUTER.
LISTEN, I HAVE TO SORT
THROUGH ALL THESE FILES--
EVERYONE BUT FINKLESTEIN.
WHEN THE NAZI PROBLEM BROKE,
HE TOOK IT KIND OF HARD.
AND THEY ALL HAVE TO BE
IN THIS EXACT ORDER,
SO YOU SHOULD GO.
LIKE, NOW.
ACTUALLY, UH...
IT'S FUNNY, I REORGANIZED
YOUR FILE STRUCTURE.
YOU WHAT?
OH, WOW.
ALL YOUR FILES
ARE THERE, JUST...
ORGANIZED.
OKAY, BYE.
UH, ETHAN, COME HERE.
I COULD TOTALLY
HELP YOU.
[GEORGE]:  THERE ARE
DEFINITE PERKS TO HAVING
SMART GUYS LIKE HIM.
I HAD TO WONDER WHAT GOOD DEED
I HAD DONE TO DESERVE THIS,
AND THEN IT DAWNED ON ME...
ETHAN!
MAYBE WITHHOLDING AFFECTION
DOES WORK A CERTAIN MAGIC.
NOT SO CLOSE.
BETH ANNE MILLER AND I
WEREN'T EXACTLY THE SAME,
BUT WE WEREN'T EXACTLY
DIFFERENT.
WE BOTH ORBITED THAT THIN AIR
LIGHT YEARS AWAY
FROM THE CENTER
OF THE SOCIAL UNIVERSE.
OKAY, FINE, WE WERE GEEKS,
BUT WHATEVER IT WAS
THAT WE SHARED,
WELL, THE TIES THAT BIND
WERE A LITTLE LOOSE THAT DAY.
[GIGGLING]
COME ON.
CAN I HELP YOU?
YEAH, I GUESS
I WANT TO, LIKE,
I DON'T KNOW, UM...
I DON'T KNOW, SWIM?
NOT LIKE THAT,
YOU'RE NOT.
I DON'T ACTUALLY
NEED TO SWIM.
I JUST WANT TO GO
INTO THE POOL TO--
NOT LIKE THAT.
[ELEVATOR MUSIC
PLAYING SOFTLY]
HI, MAY I SEE
THE SIGN-IN SHEET?
THERE ISN'T ONE.
DO YOU HAVE
AN APPOINTMENT?
PERHAPS
YOU COULD HELP ME.
I'M LOOKING FOR
AN S. SAMUELS.
THERE'S NO DR. SAMUELS
IN THIS PRACTICE.
OH. EXCUSE ME,
IS THERE AN
S. SAMUELS HERE?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK I'D LIKE
A CONSULTATION.
CAN I GET YOUR NAME?YES. DAISY.
DAISY ADAIR.
OKAY.
FILL THIS OUT, PLEASE,
AND WHAT INSURANCE
DO YOU CARRY?
I HAVE SAG.
WELL, YOU HAVE COME
TO THE RIGHT PLACE.
YEAH.
SCREEN ACTORS GUILD.
I'M AN ACTRESS.
OH.
WOW. IS SHE GOING
TO BE OKAY?
OH, SHE'LL BE FINE.
SHE'S IN THE CARE
OF DOCTORS.
[CLEARS THROAT]
IT CAN'T BE THE FACE.
NO, NO.
THESE ARE JUST FINE.
"DO YOU LOVE YOU?"
YES.
"DO YOU DESERVE
TO LOVE YOU
EVEN MORE?"
WELL, I CAN'T SEE
WHY NOT.
[♪♪]
FUCK ME.
IT'S A BUNCH
OF NAKED OLD MEN.
DO YOU KNOW WHERE
A T. HELLER IS?
OH. THEO.
IN THE SHALLOW END.
THE ONE WHO'S
YAKKING AWAY.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
YECH.
SO I'M WITH MY
SON-IN-LAW,
MR. SILICON VALLEY
HIMSELF,
AND WE'RE WATCHING
THE GAME.WHAT GAME?
GAME'S NOT IMPORTANT.
I DON'T KNOW,
SEAHAWKS,
AND HE SAYS TO ME,
"I KNOW WHY
YOUR PICTURE'S FUZZY."
YOUR PICTURE'S FUZZY?
YEAH, LIKE THE BACK
OF YOUR BALLS.
SO MR. SILICON VALLEY,
HE SAYS TO ME,
"I KNOW WHY
THE CABLE'S NO GOOD HERE."
CABLE'S
NO GOOD HERE?
HE SAYS THE PROBLEM
IS SOLAR FLARES.
"SOLAR FLARES IS CAUSING
YOUR CABLE TO GO OUT.
SOLAR FLARES IS GIVING YOU
A FUZZY PICTURE."
AND WHAT DO YOU SAY?
I SAY, "THE REASON
THE PICTURE IS FUZZY
IS I DON'T HAVE CABLE,
YOU KNOW-IT-ALL JACKASS."
[LAUGHING]
I'M DIVING.
JESUS, THEO, ENOUGH
WITH THE DIVING.
WHAT WOULD BETTY SAY?
SHE'D SAY, "LOOK AT ALL
THE TWIGS AND BERRIES."
AH, HE JUST DOES IT
FOR THE ATTENTION.
HE SHOULDN'T BE
DIVING.
MAN'S GOT
THE BLOOD PRESSURE
OF A JACKRABBIT.
HELLO.
AH.
OH, MY JESUS.
I'M, SORRY. I'VE JUST...
I JUST...
YOUR BALLS ARE HUGE.
GOD SAVE THE QUEEN.
COME ON BACK, THEO.
YOU'RE SCARING
THE CHILDREN.
RELAX, SON.
THEY'RE JUST BALLS.
SO, UH...
SO, REGGIE,
WHERE DO YOU...
WHERE DO YOU WANT
TO START?
CAN'T YOU JUST
MEET ME HERE
IN, LIKE, 20 MINUTES?
ONE THING, OKAY?
ONE THING
WE DO TOGETHER.
I'M NOT ASKING
FOR THE MOON.
YOU'LL EMBARRASS ME.
HOW? HOW WILL I
EMBARRASS YOU?
YOU'RE DOING IT
RIGHT NOW.
HOW MUCH DO I GET
TO SPEND?
NOTHING
UNTIL I SEE IT.
FINE.
REGGIE.
YOU LOOK GOOD IN BLUE.
IT MATCHES YOUR EYES.
I DON'T KNOW YOU.
OH, BOY.
WHAT WOULD
BETTY SAY?
LOOK AT HIM.
HE DOESN'T WANT
TO BE UP THERE.
SO HOW DO WE
GET HIM BACK DOWN?
WELL, WE COULD
WAVE A BRISKET.
[SNARLING]
[TRICKLING]
WHY DOES HE ALWAYS
PULL THESE STUNTS?
[CHUCKLES]
BECAUSE SOMEDAY IT'LL
MAKE A FUNNY STORY.
SOMEDAY, BUT NOT TODAY.
IT'S A BIRD.
IT'S A PLANE.
IT'S SUPER...
SHIT!
HOLY SHIT.
[CHUCKLING]
AIN'T THAT A KICK.
I DIDN'T FEEL A THING.
WELL, THAT'S BECAUSE
I TOOK YOUR SOUL OUT
BEFORE YOU HIT
THE DIVING BOARD,
SO...
SO, UH...
I'M DEAD?
THAT'S THE SITUATION?
DEAD IS THE SITUATION
YOU'RE IN, I'M AFRAID,
YEAH,
AND NOW WE'LL BE
MOVING ON.
WHAT'S THE, UH...
WHAT'S THE DEAL?
NO ONE CAN SEE ME?
NO ONE CAN SEE YOU...
APART FROM ME,
UNFORTUNATELY. I...
UGH.
I JUST CANNOT GET OVER
THE SIZE OF YOUR TESTICLES.
IMAGINE THAT, BETTY.
I GOT A GAY ANGEL.
I'M NOT ANGEL,
OR GAY.
WITH THE SIZE
OF THOSE THINGS,
IT'S NO WONDER HE
LOST HIS BALANCE!
MY FRIENDS
FOR 50 YEARS.
THEY DON'T LOOK
VERY SAD.
YOUR DEATH HASN'T
SUNK IN YET.
IT HASN'T HIT THEM
LIKE IT... HIT YOU.
THEY'RE GOING TO WANT
TO MAKE SOME KIND OF PLAQUE
HERE AT THE POOL.
"GOOD FRIEND
, GRACEFUL SWIMMER,
NOT A GOOD DIVER."
YEAH, I'M SURE THEY WILL.
IT'S GOING TO BE
HARDEST ON MARTY.
I MEAN, THIS IS GOING TO
BE ONE TOUGH EULOGY,
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
I'M SURE YOUR FUNERAL
WILL BE LOVELY.
YEAH.
I'M GOING TO NEED
TO PUT ON SOME CLOTHES.
I GOT A NICE BLUE SUIT.
BETTY'S FAVORITE.
NICE.
YEAH.
WHAT, FOR YOUR FUNERAL?
NO. NO. NO.
YOU CAN'T GO
TO YOUR OWN FUNERAL.
LOOK, PAL, NO ONE
EVER TOLD ME HOW TO LIVE,
AND I'M SURE AS HELL
NOT GOING TO START
LISTENING NOW.
I'M GOING TO MY FUNERAL.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING
FORWARD TO THIS FOR YEARS.
OH, BLOODY HELL.
GOD, CAN YOU IMAGINE
SOMEONE ACTUALLY
WEARING THAT CRAP?
SO SLUTTY.
AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED
TO SELL IT?
SHH.
COME ON.
I SO KNOW
WHAT YOU MEAN,
BUT IT'S, LIKE,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DRESS
LIKE A HOOKER
TO GET NOTICED, RIGHT?
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE, ANYWAY?
THIS STUFF IS SO NOT YOU.
YOU'RE...
BETTER THAN THAT.
HERE, LOOK AT ME
FOR A SECOND.
THIS IS IROQUOIS.
YOUR HAIR'S KIND OF
INDIAN, EXCEPT, WELL,
YOU KNOW, LIGHTER.
I'M SORRY.
THAT WAS SO
PRESUMPTUOUS OF ME.
IT'S OKAY.
YOU SURE?
OKAY.
REGGIE.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
I'VE GOT HER.
I'LL MEET YOU
RIGHT HERE
IN 20 MINUTES.
I GAVE BIRTH
TO HER, SEE,
BUT YOU'VE "GOT" HER.
THAT'S GREAT.
MY MOM'S LIKE THAT, TOO.
HYPOGLYCEMIC,
SO SHE'S TOTALLY, LIKE,
DR. JEKYLL AND MRS. HYDE.
I HAVE TO KEEP
TRISCUITS AROUND
AND JUST SHOVE THEM
IN HER MOUTH WHEN SHE
STARTS TO WIG OUT.
SO YOUR NAME'S REGGIE?
THAT'S A PRETTY
BAD-ASS NAME
FOR A GIRL.
CAN I SHOW YOU
SOMETHING REALLY PRETTY?
COME ON.
[GEORGE]:  IN A FAIR WORLD,
NICE PEOPLE WOULD BE LIKED
AND MEAN PEOPLE
WOULD BE DISLIKED,
BUT THAT'S NOT
THE WAY THINGS WORK.
UM, MILLIE,
I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU COULD FIND ME
THE AVAILABILITY STATS
FOR SCHWEGMAN'S
SUPERMARKET.
UH, NEVER MIND.
I'LL FIND THEM MYSELF.
UH, KEEP UP
THE GOOD WORK.
[GEORGE]:  IN A FAIR WORLD,
BEHAVING
LIKE A COMPLETE ASSHOLE
WOULD MAKE YOU
REALLY UNPOPULAR,
BUT THIS ISN'T A FAIR WORLD,
AND THE ASSHOLES HAVE
FOLLOWERS AND DISCIPLES
AND ASSISTANTS.
THE ASSHOLES
ARE TREATED LIKE KINGS.
SHE'S BACK.
LIKE...
SIX INCHES AWAY.
SHE SMELLS
KIND OF CITRUS-Y
AND LIKE...
WAFFLES.
I HAVE TO GO.
PERSONAL CALL, ETHAN?
SORT OF.
SOME OF THE GUYS
ON THE FIFTH FLOOR
HAD A COUPLE
OF QUESTIONS ABOUT YOU.
LIKE WHAT?
UH, WELL,
MY FRIEND SETH,
HE'S IN DATA RETRIEVAL.
SETH WANTED TO KNOW
WHAT YOUR EYES
LOOKED LIKE UP CLOSE,
SO I TOLD HIM THAT--
THEY'RE BROWN.
I SAID HAZEL...
AND KIND OF ANGRY.
NO MORE PERSONAL
CALLS, ETHAN.
OKAY. SURE. NO PROBLEM.
[GEORGE]:  IN A WORLD
WHERE PERFECTLY DECENT GIRLS
GET BRAINED
BY COSMIC SPACE SHIT
AND GET ACCUSED
OF BEING NAZI SYMPATHIZERS,
I WAS HAVING TROUBLE
TURNING THE OTHER CHEEK.
[GIGGLING]
WHAT A LOSER.
[GEORGE]:  BEING MEAN
WAS MORE FUN.
BEING MEAN WAS COOL...
YOU'RE DEAD.
AND I WAS NEVER VERY COOL.
MRS. BENSON?
IS THAT A SMILE,
SUSAN?
I CAN'T READ YOUR
FACE ANYMORE.
YOU'VE BOTOXED IT SENSELESS.
IT'S SURPRISE, SARAH.
I DIDN'T KNOW
UNTIL JUST NOW
THAT THE HUMAN BODY
CAN WITHSTAND
THAT MUCH LIPO.
TELL ME, IS IT TRUE
THE 10th ONE IS FREE?
FUCK YOU.
FUCK YOU BACK.
HOW'S IT GOING?
DR. SIMMONS SAID
THAT YOUR ASS FAT
IS PUTTING HIS DAUGHTER
THROUGH YALE.
HE'S VERY GRATEFUL.
IS EITHER OF YOU
A MRS. SAMUELS?
MIND YOUR OWN
FUCKING BUSINESS.
I'M STAN SAMUELS.
DO I KNOW YOU?
I'M DAISY.
DAISY ADAIR FROM
THE INSURANCE COMPANY.
THERE'S BEEN A MIXUP
WITH YOUR COVERAGE.
THEY'VE ALREADY MADE IT
PAINFULLY CLEAR
THAT MY PROCEDURE'S
NOT COVERED.
RIGHT. IT'S NOT.
WHY DID YOU ASK
FOR A MRS. SAMUELS?
I JUST ASSUMED
YOU WERE GOING TO BE A WOMAN.
I WILL BE SOON.
I HOPE.
OF COURSE YOU WILL.
I SAW YOU PARKED YOUR JAG
IN THE HANDICAP ZONE, SARAH.
IS CELLULITE
NOW A RECOGNIZED HANDICAP?
TRAMP.
TART.SLUT.
MIDDLE-AGED.
CAN I HELP YOU?
OH, NO, I'M JUST BROWSING.
OKAY, WELL, JUST LET ME
KNOW IF YOU WANT TO TAKE
ANYTHING FOR A TEST DRIVE.
YOU KNOW,
IT MIGHT BE TIME
TO TRY A NEW PRODUCT OR TWO.
OKAY, WELL,
IT'S LIKE YOUR HOUSE,
SO YOU START
FROM THE FOUNDATIONS,
THEN YOU BUILD
FROM THE GROUND UP,
SO FOR EXAMPLE,
WE HAVE "HATE YOUR HUSBAND
BUT WILLING TO STAY NEUTRAL,"
OR...
"ALREADY KICKED HIS ASS
TO THE CURB."
WHAT SHADE IS,
"HE'S BANGING ONE
OF HIS STUDENTS"?
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
JOY.THAT'S A PRETTY NAME.
SO, WHAT DO YOU WANT, JOY?
THE LAST 10 YEARS
OF MY LIFE BACK.
I CAN DO THAT.
[GEORGE]:  PART OF ME KNEW
THAT BEING MEAN WAS RECKLESS,
THAT IT WAS
KIND OF LIKE DRIVING TOO FAST.
SO WHAT IF I WASN'T
WEARING MY SEAT BELT?
SO WHAT IF I OCCASIONALLY
SCRAPED ANOTHER FENDER?
JESUS CHRIST, CRYSTAL!
I'M SORRY, MILLIE.
PEOPLE HAVE TO WALK
AROUND HERE, YOU KNOW,
AND I DON'T HAVE TIME
TO PICK THIS CRAP UP.
NICE GIRLS DON'T GET THE GUY.
NICE GIRLS DON'T RISE
TO THE TOP.
[GRUNTS]
NOW YOU'VE
MADE ME MAD.
NOW WE CAN
NEVER BE FRIENDS.
[GEORGE]:  NICE GIRLS
FINISH LAST.
THEO.
THEO. THEO.
WE HAVE
THESE RULES, OKAY?
NO FUNERALS.
FUNERALS ARE
FOR THE LIVING,
SO THEY TAKE
A COUPLE OF DAYS
TO ARRANGE--
OH, ESPECIALLY
ONE LIKE MINE.
OH, IT'S GOING TO BE
AN EVENT.
I HAD FRIENDS.
I CAN'T WAIT.
THAT'S JUST IT, THEO.
YOU CAN'T WAIT.
YOU SEE, UH...
OH, GOODNESS,
HOW DO I
EXPLAIN THIS?
IT'S, UH...
YOU'VE CALLED
THE CABLE GUY, RIGHT?
AND YOU'VE MADE
AN APPOINTMENT,
AND THAT CABLE GUY
HAS MADE A WINDOW
FOR YOU,
AND THAT WINDOW IS
FROM 12:00 TO 5:00.
RIGHT?
SO IF YOU'RE NOT THERE
WHEN HE PRESSES
THAT LITTLE DOORBELL,
THEN...
NO CABLE, HUH?
I DON'T BLOODY KNOW,
THEO.
I REALLY BLOODY
DON'T KNOW.
SON, I APPRECIATE
THE EFFORT,
BUT I WAS IN SALES,
AND I GOT TO TELL YOU,
YOU'RE NOT CLOSING.
I'M GOING TO MY FUNERAL.
PLEASE AT LEAST
MEET MY BOSS, THEN.
OH, LOOK AT THIS, BETTY.
I'M TALKING TO GOD TODAY.
NO, HE JUST THINKS HE'S GOD.
YOU'RE SURE
NO ONE CAN SEE ME?
OH, UH... NO, NO.
I WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
THAT WAS COMPLETELY
OBVIOUS BY NOW.
AND THAT JUST
IS NOT RIGHT FOR THEM.
OKAY?
HI.
THEO...
WHEN DO THEY CALL
MY PARENTS?
ARE THEY YOUR
NEXT OF KIN?
DID YOUR PARENTS KNOW
WHAT YOU WERE DOING?
THAT'S A BEAUTIFUL CROSS.
ARE YOU CATHOLIC?
I'M THINKING ABOUT IT.
WHEN I WAS A KID,
MY MOM USED TO PRAY
AT THE DROP OF A HAT.
EVERY MORNING
BEFORE MY DAD
WOULD GO TO WORK,
EVERY TIME
I TOOK A TEST...
FOR THE POT ROAST
BEING TENDER.
SHE REALLY NEVER
STOPPED PRAYING.
THE POWER OF PRAYER
IS VERY REAL
FOR SOME PEOPLE.
YEAH, WELL,
A MILLION HAIL MARYS
DIDN'T TURN ME
INTO A GIRL.
I'M SORRY.
DO YOU THINK
THERE'S A CHANCE
I COULD I GO TO CHURCH
ONE LAST TIME?
OF COURSE.
I'M NOT INTERESTED
IN SPECULATION, DOCTOR.
I'M INTERESTED
IN FACTS.
THE FACT IS,
YOU HAVE NO CHIN.
YOU NEED
A CHIN IMPLANT.
I MEAN, LOOK AT YOU.
HOW DO YOU...
HOW DO YOU EVEN
CHANGE PILLOW CASES?
AND THAT
IS EVERYTHING.
NOW, REGGIE,
IF YOU CHANGE YOUR
MIND OR WHATEVER,
THAT'S COMPLETELY COOL.
WOW, CHECK OUT
YOUR MOM.
WELL?
YOU LOOK LIKE A NEWSCASTER.
HOW MUCH?
195, PLUS TAX.
YOU'RE GOOD.
REGGIE!
REGGIE, STOP.
HI.
HELLO.
DO I KNOW YOU?
NO. I'M STEVE.
YOU'RE HOT.
FUCK OFF, STEVE.
WHO WAS THAT?
NOBODY.
NEWSCASTER, MY ASS.
SO EVERYTHING'S
ON YOUR HARD DRIVE,
AND I MADE YOU
A HARD COPY
IN THIS BINDER,
IN CASE, YOU KNOW,
THAT WHOLE NAZI
PROBLEM RESURFACES.GOOD.
WHY ARE THERE POST-ITS
ON MY BINDER?
I PUT THESE POST-ITS
AT THE TOP OF
EACH SUB-SECTION,
SO THAT IF, LIKE,
SAY YOU WERE TRYING
TO FIND A JOB FOR SOMEONE
WHO COULD TYPE AND ALSO DRIVE,
THEN YOU COULD JUST--
I DON'T LIKE POST-ITS.
OKAY. I JUST--
LOSE THE POST-ITS,
ETHAN.
OKAY, SURE.
SO, I DO ORIGAMI.
I REALLY LIKE CRAFTS,
AND I HAD
SOME EXTRA TIME
BECAUSE
I WORK SO QUICKLY
SO I MADE YOU...
I MADE YOU A SWAN.
OH.
ETHAN.
OH, THAT'S SO SWEET.
I'M SORRY.
YEAH.
IT WAS A PRETTY ONE.
UM, I GUESS
I COULD MAKE YOU
ANOTHER ONE.
THAT'S OKAY.
I DIDN'T REALLY
WANT TO ANYWAY.
OKAY, BYE.
[GEORGE]:  I WASN'T
ALWAYS LIKE THIS.
I USED TO BE A NICE PERSON.
HI, BETH ANNE.
ISN'T IT WEIRD
HOW THERE'S SO MANY WAVES
BUT THE WATER'S
NOT REALLY GOING ANYWHERE?
WHY CAN'T YOU
JUST BE NORMAL?
WHY DO YOU HAVE
TO BE SO WEIRD?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT BEING NICE
DIDN'T SEEM TO WORK EITHER.
IT'S LIKE ANY WAY I PLAY IT...
I WIND UP ALONE.
I'M SORRY, DELORES.
YOU KNOW, MILLIE,
BACK IN THE DAYS WHEN
I HAD ALL THOSE RESTRAINING
ORDERS AGAINST ME,
I THOUGHT HATE
WAS THE ANSWER.
SERIOUSLY, DELORES,
I'M NOT A NAZI.
OH, I KNOW THAT, SILLY.
I'M JUST TRYING TO SAY,
SOMETIMES WHEN I HAVE
TO CHOOSE BETWEEN
A BULLWHIP AND A SMILE,
I CHOOSE THE SMILE.
THAT WAS ONE
OF THE FIRST THINGS
YOU EVER SAID TO ME.
HMM?
YOU SAID, "I HAVEN'T
SEEN YOU SMILE ONCE."
I DON'T THINK SO.
I SAID THAT
TO ANOTHER YOUNG GIRL.
LOVELY YOUNG GIRL.
TRAGIC WHAT HAPPENED.
YEAH, MY MISTAKE.
MILLIE...
ETHAN JUST QUIT.
WHAT?
HE SAID
HE WASN'T CUT OUT
FOR THIS KIND
OF CORPORATE
CUT-THROAT CULTURE.
WHAT HAPPENED, MILLIE?
I HAD A BAD DAY.
NO. MILLIE...
ETHAN HAD A BAD DAY.
THIS PARK'S BEAUTIFUL.
ALL OF GOD'S
CREATURES, RIGHT?
I GUESS.
I WANTED TO BE
A GIRL...
EVER SINCE
I CAN REMEMBER.
WHO WOULDN'T
WANT TO BE A GIRL?
WE'RE SO MUCH
PRETTIER THAN BOYS.
YOU'RE KIND OF PRETTY.
YOU MAKE IT LOOK
SO EFFORTLESS.
YEAH, DON'T LET
THE FINAL PICTURE
FOOL YOU.
THIS IS TWO HOURS
OF HARD LABOR
IN THE MORNING.
NO, IT'S IN
EVERYTHING YOU DO.
THE WAY YOU WALK,
THE WAY YOUR HAIR
FLOWS,
THE WAY YOU MOVE
YOUR HIPS.
IT'S PERFECT.
ARE YOU FLIRTING
WITH ME?
I'M DEAD.
RIGHT.
STILL,
YOURS IS THE FACE
I WANTED TO SEE
IN THE MIRROR
EVERY MORNING.
YOU'RE JUST PERFECT.
I KNOW,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT,
STAN? SO ARE YOU.
I THINK WE BOTH KNOW
THAT'S NOT QUITE TRUE.
YOU'RE SWEET.
YOU'RE HONEST.
YOU'VE GOT GREAT STYLE.
YOU'D HAVE MADE
A GOOD WOMAN.
WOULD'VE, COULD'VE.
I GOT SCREWED.
YEAH.
IT'S ALL
PART OF HIS PLAN.
THAT'S WHAT THEY SAY.
WHY ARE YOU
GOING TO CHURCH?
IT'S WHERE YOU
TALK TO GOD, DAISY.
IT'S HIS HOUSE.
REGGIE,
I NEED TO GET A MOVE ON
EARLY TOMORROW MORNING,
SO YOU'RE
GOING TO HAVE TO...
WOW.
DON'T YOU KNOCK?
WOW, YOU LOOK
LIKE A...
YOUNG WOMAN.
PLEASE GET OUT.
I'M OUT.
THANKS.
MATZOH BALLS
ARE NICE TONIGHT.
DO YOU CARE IF
PEOPLE LIKE YOU?
DO I ACT
LIKE I CARE?
NO.
NOBODY LIKES COPS ANYWAY,
BUT THEY SURE ARE
HAPPY TO SEE US
WHEN THE SHIT
HITS THE FAN.
EAT YOUR SOUP
BEFORE IT GETS COLD.
JESUS, THOSE ARE
SOME ENORMOUS BALLS.
EXCUSE ME?
OH, GOOD GOD!
YOU HAVE TO HELP ME.
THIS MAN WANTS TO GO
TO HIS OWN FUNERAL.
HE DIED NAKED?
SMASHED INTO
A DIVING BOARD.
WITH HIS BALLS?
STUNNING, ISN'T IT?TELL HIM THE RULES, MASON.
NO FUNERALS.
I'VE TRIED THAT, RUBE.
THE THING IS--
THE THING IS WHAT, MASON?
YOU KNOW, THAT THING...
YOU'RE GOOD AT THAT.
THE THING
THAT YOU CAN...
YOU'RE BETTER AT...
JUST, YOU KNOW,
YOU KNOW...
THE TALKING.
WELL SAID.
PLEASE, RUBE.
HIS NAME'S THEO.
THAT'S JUST
TOO MUCH BALL.
NOW HE'S PUT ME
OFF MY SOUP.
SO YOU SEE
WHAT I'M SAYING?
I DON'T SEE WHAT
YOU'RE SAYING, MASON.
I DO.
OH, GOD.
DER WAFFLE HAUS.
I REMEMBER WHEN
THE FIRST ONE OF
THESE WENT UP.
THE WAR WAS OVER.
IT DIDN'T GO SO WELL
IN THE BEGINNING.
BETTY AND I
WERE ON OUR FIFTH DATE.
SHE HAD WAFFLES.
THANKS.
THANKS A MILLION.
COME ON, THEO.
LET'S CHAT.
OH, LOOK
AT THE LOVEBIRDS.
KISS HER, YOU PUTZ.
THIS WAY, THEO.
ARE YOU GOING
TO EAT THAT SOUP?
THAT'S JUST GROSS.
YOU HAVEN'T SEEN
MANY OF THEM,
HAVE YOU?
MY FIRST... PAIR.
THEY'RE NOT ALL LIKE THAT.
SOME ARE WORSE.
POOR BETTY.
WHO'S BETTY?
NO ONE.
HOW DOES THIS GUY
NOT CARE
IF PEOPLE SEE HIM
LIKE THAT?
HE JUST DOESN'T.
DO YOU CARE
IF PEOPLE LIKE YOU?
NO.
WHY? HAS SOMEBODY SAID
SOMETHING ABOUT ME?
IS IT DAISY?
DOES SHE NOT LIKE ME?
I HAVE TO GO.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
WHAT, HAS DAISY SAID
SOMETHING ABOUT ME?
THAT OLD MAN IS
YOUR REAP, MASON.
SO BLOODY WHAT?
MAN, YOU NEVER
MET A PROBLEM
YOU COULDN'T
RUN FROM, HUH?
YOU'RE THE ONE
THAT NEEDS SOME BALLS.
'NIGHT, RUBE.
CAN SHE SEE ME?
SHE CAN,
AND SHE'LL NEVER BE
THE SAME FOR IT.
YOU KNOW, THEO,
DEATH HAS
ITS OWN PROTOCOL.
IT'S LIKE A TRAIN.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO BE LATE FOR YOUR TRAIN.
EXACTLY WHAT THAT
MASON GUY SAID,
EXCEPT PRETTIER.
THANK YOU.
WHY DO YOU WANT TO GO
TO YOUR FUNERAL?
WELL...
I'M JUST CURIOUS
TO SEE WHO COMES,
HEAR WHAT PEOPLE
HAVE TO SAY.
I LIVED A LONG LIFE,
YOU KNOW.
STORIES WILL BE TOLD.
YOU'RE WORRIED SOMEBODY
MIGHT MAKE A JOKE OR TWO
AT YOUR EXPENSE?
I DON'T...
I DON'T KNOW.
I WAS A LOUDMOUTH.
BETTY ALWAYS LAUGHED
AT MY JOKES.
YOU KNOW, THEO,
YOU STRIKE ME
AS THE KIND OF GUY
WHO WAS WHO HE WAS,
NOT A LOT OF BULLSHIT.
YOU WERE THE KIND OF GUY
WHO DIDN'T GIVE A SHIT
ABOUT BEING LIKED.
THAT'S WHY PEOPLE
LIKED HIM.
HOW...
HOW LONG AGO DID
BETTY DIE, THEO?
SEVEN YEARS THIS NOVEMBER.
I'M SORRY, I'M...
I'M A BIT CONFUSED.
I MEAN, ISN'T SHE
THE ONE THAT YOU'D
REALLY WANT TO SEE?
AND I'M THINKING
SHE'S NOT GOING TO BE
AT YOUR FUNERAL.
YEAH.
I MISS HER.
I MISS MY WIFE.
I DON'T THINK WE
SHOULD KEEP BETTY
WAITING ANY LONGER.
LET'S GO FIND HER,
THEN, EH?
COME ON.
RUBE, DO YOU THINK
DAISY'S UPSET WITH
ME FOR ANY REASON?
I CAN'T IMAGINE
WHY SHE WOULD BE.
COME ON, ALREADY.
I'M FREEZING
MY BALLS OFF HERE.
SORRY, THEO.
WOULDN'T WANT TO
KEEP YOU WAITING.
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME
TIME ALONE, STAN?
PLEASE.
[♪♪]
YOU BASTARD.
STAN!
HYPOCRITICAL,
NO-GOOD,
BACKSTABBING,
JUDGMENTAL...
YOU SAID WE'RE ALL
GOD'S CHILDREN.
EXCEPT THE FREAKS.
EXCEPT FOR ME.
YOU. YOU DO IT.
I CAN'T. I WON'T.
JUST HELP ME.
I'M SORRY. I CAN'T.
WHY WOULD GOD
DO THIS TO ME?
DO WHAT?
HAVE YOU DIE THIS WAY?
HAVE ME LIVE THIS WAY.
GOD DOESN'T LOVE
ALL CREATURES, DAISY.
I THINK YOU SHOULD
PRAY, STAN.
I WANT TO FORGIVE HIM,
BUT I WANT HIM
TO TELL ME...
THAT HE'S SORRY FIRST.
[GLASS SHATTERING]
[SOFT WHOOSHING]
COME ON! GO! GO!
HEY, HEY!
HEY, GOD'S WATCHING YOU!
HE SAW THAT!
HOOLIGANS!
YOU'LL PAY FOR THAT!
STAN?
STAN...
BLESSED ART THOU
AMONGST WOMEN.
[♪♪]
[GEORGE]:  I DON'T KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT MAKES PEOPLE CROSS OVER.
I MEAN, SOULS.
I THINK THEY SEE LIGHT
WHERE OTHERS CANNOT.
I THINK THEY SEE A CHANCE
TO BECOME SOMETHING ELSE.
SOMEONE ELSE.
SOME PEOPLE ARE BECOMING
WHO THEY'RE GOING TO BE,
OTHERS ARE JUST TRYING TO BE
ANYTHING BUT WHO THEY ARE...
AND OTHERS JUST CAN'T DECIDE.
THIS IS IROQUOIS.
IT'LL MATCH YOUR
DARK HAIR PERFECTLY.
[GEORGE]:  EVERYBODY
WANTS TO BE LIKED.
I KNOW I DID...
BUT I KNEW
I WAS STILL LOOKING...
FOR SOMETHING,
FOR SOMEONE.
FOR LIGHT...
UM, HI, GEORGE.
HI, BETH ANNE.
AND I HAD NO IDEA
WHERE I'D FIND IT.
WHEN I WAS 10,
SOMETHING HAPPENED TO ME...
[LAUGHING]
AND SOMETHING HAPPENED
TO BETH ANNE MILLER...
AND IT CHANGED
BOTH OF OUR LIVES...
FOREVER.