[♪♪]
I LOVED HALLOWEEN.
OKAY, NOT A HUGE
SURPRISE THERE.
I MEAN, WHAT KID
DOESN'T LOVE HALLOWEEN?
BUT MY DEVOTION TO THE DAY
WAS NOT
FOR THE OBVIOUS REASONS.
I COULDN'T CARE LESS
ABOUT THE CANDY.
AND I DIDN'T GIVE A SHIT
ABOUT THE COSTUMES.
I LOVED HALLOWEEN
BECAUSE I LOVED LOOKING
INTO OTHER PEOPLE'S HOUSES.
WHY'S THE CANDY OUTSIDE?
THEY PROBABLY DON'T WANT
TO BE DISTURBED, SWEETIE.
BUT IT'S HALLOWEEN,
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE
DISTURBING.
MAYBE THEY'RE JUST NOT HOME.
THAT'S A BUNCH OF BULL--
THEY'RE HOME!
[SIGHING][RINGING]
TRICK OR TREAT,
DAMNIT!
[RINGING]
JUST TAKE A PIECE OF CANDY
AND LET'S GO
TO THE NEXT HOUSE.
HELLO!
I KNOW YOU'RE IN THERE!
GEORGE, LISTEN
TO YOUR MOTHER.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
EVERY OTHER KID
IS IN IT FOR THE CANDY.
SO? SHE'S CURIOUS.
CURIOUS IS GOOD.
HEY, GEORGIA,
I HAVE A FEELING
THE NEXT HOUSE
IS GOING TO BE
GIVING OUT GUMMY WORMS.
MM-HMM. AND I THINK
THEY'RE GOING TO LET YOU
SEE INSIDE.
THERE'S BARELY ANY FURNITURE.
MAYBE SOME WEIRDO LIVES HERE.
HONEY, YOU'RE BEING
THE WEIRDO.
WE'RE LEAVING.
COME IF YOU WANT.
FINE!
BOO!
HALLOWEEN IS WHEN THE FREAKS
CAME OUT OF THE SHADOWS.
NOW THAT I'M OLDER...
AND DEADER,
I SEE THAT HALLOWEEN
IS AMATEUR NIGHT FOR DEATH.
"OOH, LOOK AT ME,
I'M BLEEDING."
SOMEONE HIT ME WITH AN AX."
TRICK OR TREAT.TRICK OR TREAT.
YOU KNOW,
I'VE SEEN ONE OF THOSE
IN REAL LIFE,
AND LET ME
TELL YOU SOMETHING--
NOT SO FUNNY.
I'M NOT A PRUDE.
IT'S JUST UNSEEMLY.
A MAN'S HOME IS
A MAN'S CASTLE.
IN HIS CASTLE,
HE SHOULD BE ALLOWED
TO SWING FREE.
THERE ARE BOUNDARIES.
MASON, OTHER PEOPLE
CAN SEE THEM.
WHY CAN'T YOU?
NUDE IS NATURAL.
NUDE IS NOW.
I'M ABOUT TO EAT BREAKFAST,
SO CAN WE EASE UP
ON THE NAKED TALK?
PLEASE?
THANK YOU.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO
SEE IT, GEORGIA.
IT'S NOT HOW I WANTED
TO START MY DAY.
WELL, YOU SCREAMING
AT 6:53 IN THE MORNING
WAS NOT HOW I WANTED
TO START MINE.
BY THE WAY,
YOU'RE NOT THE FIRST WOMAN
WHO HAS SHRIEKED AT THE SIGHT
OF THE LOCH NESS MONSTER
RISING TO THE SURFACE.
DON'T FLATTER YOURSELF.
OKAY, FOLKS,
TWO RULES STARTING
AS OF RIGHT NOW.
ONE--
BREAKFAST AT OUR HOUSE
IS NO LONGER
CLOTHING OPTIONAL.
ALL MEALS.ALL MEALS.
FINE.
TWO, AND MOST IMPORTANT--
YOU TOUCH
MY FUCKING POP TARTS AGAIN
AND YOUR "MONSTER"
IS GOING TO GET IT
IN HIS SLEEP.
FINE, AND F.Y.I., I LIKE
STRAWBERRY FROSTED THE BEST.
IN ADDITION
TO EATING MY GROCERIES,
YOU MIGHT WANT
TO START PROVIDING THEM.
YOU NEED TO EARN YOUR KEEP.
I--
ALL RIGHT!
ALL RIGHT...
I--I'LL DO SOME CHORES.
OKAY, FINE, DO SOME CHORES.
DO MY FUCKING LAUNDRY.
I DON'T THINK SO.
DO YOU LIKE CANDY?
EVERYONE LIKES CANDY.
EXCELLENT. WELL,
THIS IS WHAT I'M
GOING TO DO.
I'M GOING TO GET
SO MUCH CANDY TONIGHT,
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
A WHOLE YEAR'S SUPPLY
IN OUR HOUSE.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
SO MUCH CANDY,
YOU'RE GOING TO BE BEGGING
FOR CANDY MERCY.
OH, I'M GOING TO START NOW.
KIDS, OVER HERE.
KIDDIES, HERE.
NO, MASON,
DON'T BRING CHILDREN
NEAR US.
HI.
OKAY, LISTEN.
WE'RE GOING TO PLAY
A LITTLE HALLOWEEN GAME.
NOW, I'M GOING TO ASK YOU
A QUESTION,
AND YOU ARE GOING TO
ANSWER ME.
IF YOU GET IT RIGHT,
YOU GET A DOLLAR.
IF YOU GET IT WRONG,
I GET YOUR CANDY. ALL RIGHT?
RIGHT. QUESTION--
WHAT ORIGINAL MEMBER
OF THE ROLLING STONES
CROAKED WHILST HAVING
A DROWNING ACCIDENT?
MICK JAGGER.
NO, HE'S KIND OF ALIVE
AND STILL TOURING.
KEITH MOON?NO! THAT'S THE FUCKING WHO.
WHO?THE WHO.
IT'S BRIAN JONES,
NOW HAND OVER THE CANDY.
NOW PISS OFF.
I PARTIED WITH HIM,
AND I REAPED HIM.
YES!
STEALING CANDY
FROM CHILDREN?
MM. CHALLENGING.
YOU'VE COME
A LONG WAY, MASON.
IT'S HALLOWEEN,
RUBY.
WORSE THINGS
WILL HAPPEN TODAY.
IN FACT, THEY WILL.
YOU. YOU.
AND YOU.
GIVE ME
A LITTLE ROOM, HUH?
AND YOU...
MIGHT WANT
TO WEAR THIS.UM...
I KNOW I'M THE YOUNGEST
ONE HERE,
BUT I DON'T
TRICK-OR-TREAT.
NO, NO.
REAPER LEGEND--
THE DEAD WILL APPEAR
AS THEMSELVES
ON HALLOWEEN.
SO, IN THEORY, I CAN BE...
RECOGNIZED.I'VE NEVER BOUGHT THAT.
I DON'T CARE
WHETHER YOU BUY IT OR NOT.
OPEN YOURSELF TO THE
POSSIBILITY THAT THERE ARE
PEOPLE OUT THERE
WHO KNEW YOU
WHEN YOU WERE ALIVE
AND WHO CAN SEE YOU TODAY
AS YOU WERE.
I'VE BEEN DEAD
FOR OVER 60 YEARS.
I'M NOT TALKING TO YOU.
SHE'S DEAD A YEAR,
IN HER HOMETOWN.
YEAH, IT'S NONSENSE, OKAY?
AND WHY WOULD YOU WANT TO
PUT THIS EXQUISITE FACE
BEHIND A MASK?
YEAH.
AND THESE STRAPPY THINGS
GET CAUGHT IN MY HAIR.
IT'S VERY PAINFUL.
[WHISTLES]
WOW.WOW.
NICE...
I'M UNDERCOVER TODAY,
AND I DON'T WANT TO HEAR IT.
ROXY, YOUR DRESS
MAKES ME FEEL FUNNY
IN MY PANTS.
I'M ARMED,
AND YOU'RE NOT.
DO WE HAVE TO GO DOWN
THIS ROAD AGAIN?
NO.JUST CURIOUS--
WHERE IS YOUR FIREARM?
OH.
WHAT EXACTLY ARE YOU
SUPPOSED TO BE?
I'M ROXY,
THE BAD-ASS WITCH
OF THE NORTHWEST.
HEY...
BOTH OF OUR POST-ITS
ARE AT 59 PAST THE HOUR.
MINE, TOO.
WHY ISN'T SHE
WEARING A MASK?
FUCKS WITH HER HAIR.
HAPPY HALLOWEEN.
HAPPY HALLOWEEN.BYE.
HOW MUCH?
OKAY.BOO!
KEEP THE CHANGE,
KIFFANY.
IS THAT REAPER LEGEND
REALLY TRUE?
WELL, IT'S AS TRUE
AS YOU WANT IT TO BE.
WHAT, THAT'S IT?
THAT'S ALL YOU GOT?
I COULD MARCH RIGHT UP
TO MY OLD HOUSE
AND ASK MY SISTER
FOR A KIT KAT.
YOU COULD.
WHAT'S STOPPING ME?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT IS STOPPING YOU?
SOMETHING HAPPENED TO YOU.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
YOU'RE THE PATERNAL ONE.
IS THAT WHAT I AM?
YES.
DAISY'S THE STARLET,
MASON'S THE SCREW-UP,
ROXY'S...
ROXY, AND YOU'RE...
YOU'RE THE DAD.
WELL, PATERNAL DIDN'T TURN OUT
TO BE SUCH A GOOD GIG.
YOU WANT ADVICE FROM ME,
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
HEY, WEAR RUNNING SHOES TODAY.
TRICK-OR-TREATING'S
A REAL GRIND.
BOO!
I HAVE TO GO
TO HAPPY TIME.
IT'S SUNDAY.
I LEFT MY
RUNNING SHOES THERE.
I'LL COME WITH YOU.
ROXY'S THE MOTHER.
EXCUSE ME?
SHE REMINDS ME OF MY MOTHER.
SHE REMINDS ME
OF MY MOTHER.
WAS SHE A COP?
SHE COULD HAVE BEEN.
OH, THESE SEEDS
ARE GROSS.
SLIMY.
WAIT TILL
THEY'RE TOASTED.
YOU'LL LOVE THEM.
WHY CAN'T I
CARVE THE PUMPKIN?
MAYBE NEXT YEAR.
THAT'S WHAT YOU SAID
LAST YEAR.
WHY DON'T YOU GO GET
YOUR COSTUME READY
FOR TONIGHT?
I'M NOT GOING
TRICK-OR-TREATING.
BUT YOU LOVE CANDY.
I'M OVER IT.
YOUR SISTER
WENT TRICK-OR-TREATING
EVERY YEAR,
AND SHE TOOK YOU.
I'LL BET SHE'LL BE
OUT THERE TONIGHT.
REGGIE.
IT'S HALLOWEEN--
THE NIGHT WHEN GHOSTS
WALK THE EARTH.
OKAY, I'M BRINGING THIS UP
IN THERAPY TODAY.
DANA'S COMING IN
AS A FAVOR.
I WAS JUST KIDDING.
OH. OKAY.
WERE YOU?
WE CAN GO
TRICK-OR-TREATING
TONIGHT IF YOU WANT.
FINE. ARE YOU GOING TO WEAR
YOUR POCHAHONTAS OUTFIT?
I THINK I'M GOING TO GO
AS A GHOST.
WE DON'T HAVE
A GHOST COSTUME.
GHOSTS DON'T WEAR COSTUMES.
THEY LOOK JUST LIKE
YOU AND ME.
ONE HALLOWEEN,
WHEN I WAS A LITTLE KID,
MY DAD PULLED OUT A KNIFE
TO CARVE OUR PUMPKIN...
I TOTALLY LOST IT,
I STARTED TO CRY,
BEGGED HIM
NOT TO HURT THE PUMPKIN.
[MAN WHISTLING]
MY MOM AND DAD TOLD ME
TO CALM DOWN.
THEY TOLD ME
THE SCARY STUFF ON HALLOWEEN
WAS ALL MAKE-BELIEVE,
THAT NO ONE WOULD GET HURT,
LEAST OF ALL THE PUMPKIN.
I MEAN, THEY'RE YOUR PARENTS.
YOU HAVE TO TRUST
YOUR PARENTS.
AND THEN I LET THEM
KILL THE PUMPKIN.
WHAT THE FUCK?
EVERY YEAR. EVERY YEAR.
I HATE HALLOWEEN.
EVERY JACKASS
WITH A 50-CENT MASK
THINKS HE HAS A LICENSE
FOR MAYHEM AND TOMFOOLERY.
ALREADY TODAY,
I HAD A DEAD CAT
AND A BAG
OF FLAMING SHIT
ON SOME OLD LADY'S
DOORSTEP.
FLAMING SHIT.
THAT'S A CLASSIC.
THIS PRINCESS GARB
IS SO UNCOMFORTABLE.
I'M TAKING THIS OFF.
NO, NO, NO, ROXY,
THAT MAKES THE
WHOLE ENSEMBLE.
GOD, YOU LOOK GREAT.
MAYBE I WILL PUT
A COSTUME TOGETHER.
BE RIGHT BACK.
IF YOU KEEP EATING
ALL THE CANDY,
HOW ARE WE GOING TO HAVE
A YEAR'S SUPPLY LEFT
BY THE END
OF THE EVENING?
WELL, IF YOU'LL COME WITH ME
ON MY LITTLE TRIP
OF CONTROLLED CHAOS,
THEN YOU'LL SEE.
I'M IN.
JUST OUT OF RESPECT
FOR THE EVENING.
YEAH?
IT'S HOODLUMS LIKE YOU
THAT MAKE MY JOB
SO DIFFICULT.
OH, ROXY.
LET ME EXPLAIN
SOMETHING TO YOU.
THE UNIVERSE,
IN ALL OF ITS
INFINITE WISDOM,
ALLOWS THE FORCES
OF DESTRUCTION
ONE EVENING A YEAR
TO HAVE FULL REIGN.
ON ALL HALLOWS' EVE,
YOU CAN GET AWAY
WITH ANYTHING.
CAN WE LOOK IN
PEOPLE'S HOUSES?
YES.[BOTH SNICKERING]
CAN'T BLOODY WAIT!
OOH.
OH. ONE CAN GET AWAY
WITH MURDER.
[MAN WHISTLING]
I NEVER BELIEVED
IN FAIRIES.
I NEVER CLAPPED
FOR TINKERBELL,
AND I WAS NEVER SCARED
OF GHOSTS.
BUT MAYBE THERE WAS MORE
TO HALLOWEEN THAN
MILK DUDS AND VANDALISM.
MAYBE THERE WAS A REASON
FOR ME TO STAY IN THE SHADOWS.
NOW, THAT'S ALMOST
DEFINITELY BULLSHIT.
HELLO, HAPPY TIME!
SHH!
IT'S SO STRANGE
THAT YOU WERE HERE, MILLIE.
I AM HERE.
NO, I MEAN BEFORE.
NOW IT'S ALMOST LIKE
YOU'RE HAUNTING THE PLACE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I AM STEALING THESE
FOR CANDY-GATHERING
PURPOSES.
WELL, COULD YOU EASE UP
ON THE LARCENY?
I WORK HERE.
I AM SIMPLY TESTING
FOR CANDY-GATHERING CAPACITY.
WE HAVE A WINNER.
LOVELY.
I WAS WATCHING T.V.
LAST NIGHT,
SOME COPS AND ROBBERS
AND LAWYER BULLSHIT.
YEAH, I KNOW, I HEARD YOU.
YOU WOKE ME UP.
IT WAS SOME  LAW AND ORDER
RERUN BULLSHIT,
AND, UH,
THERE WAS A DETECTIVE
ASKING QUESTIONS
TO A PERP, RIGHT?
AND IT ALWAYS
BLOODY ANNOYS ME
SO FUCKING MUCH,
BECAUSE IT'S THE SAME
FUCKING QUESTION
AGAIN AND AGAIN
AND AGAIN.
"DID YOU KNOW
THE DECEASED?"
EXACTLY--
"DID YOU KNOW THE DECEASED?"
COME ON. I MEAN, EVERYBODY
IN THE WHOLE FUCKING WORLD
KNOWS THE ANSWER IS "NO."
THE ANSWER
IS ALWAYS "NO."
ALWAYS "NO."
NO, NO, NO, NO.OKAY, I GOT IT.
I THINK THEY SHOULD ASK US
THAT QUESTION.
"DID YOU KNOW THE DECEASED?"
"NO, I DIDN'T KNOW
THE BLOODY DECEASED,
"BECAUSE
I'VE JUST MET HER
"I'M ABOUT TO REAP HER,
AND SHE'S GOING TO DIE
IN THREE MINUTES."
LIKE YOU DID, HERE.
I WAS HERE A COUPLE OF HOURS.
A MORNING, ACTUALLY,
AND NO ONE KNEW ME.
I DON'T WANT TO KNOW
THE DECEASED.
NEVER HAVE.
YEAH, ME EITHER.
I ONLY WANT TO KNOW
PEOPLE WHO'VE BEEN DEAD
A LONG TIME.
ME, TOO.
EXCEPT FOR YOU.
[GASPS]
NICE COSTUME, CRYSTAL.
SPOOKY.
NICE MASK, MILLIE.
THANKS.
WHAT'VE YOU
GOT THERE, CRYSTAL?
NOTHING.
IS IT A...
TRICK-OR-TREATING MAP?
HAVE YOU GOT
PRIME CANDY ZONES
HIGHLIGHTED?
MASON,
LET'S GO NOW.
HAPPY HALLOWEEN, CRYSTAL.
LET'S GO, MASON.
[♪♪]
DEATH IS LIKE GOING TO
YOUR FIRST HAUNTED HOUSE
WHEN YOU WERE A KID...
[WHISTLING]
YOU HAD TO WALK THROUGH IT
TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT STUFF WAS REALLY SCARY,
AND WHAT STUFF
WAS JUST IN YOUR HEAD.
SO, HOW ARE WE
ON THIS HALLOWEEN SUNDAY?
HOW ARE YOU FEELING
ABOUT THE DOG?
THE DOG HAS A NAME.
J.D.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING
ABOUT J.D.?
WHERE'S THE CANDY?
REGGIE.
WHAT? CRAZY GIRLS DON'T NEED
A LITTLE CHOCOLATE?
YOU KNOW, REGGIE,
HOLIDAYS CAN BE
A LOT OF FUN,
BUT THEY'RE ALSO
EMOTIONALLY DIFFICULT,
AND IT'S HARD NOT TO THINK
ABOUT YOUR FAMILY.
ABOUT GEORGE.
WELL, DID GEORGE
LIKE HALLOWEEN?
GEORGE LOVED HALLOWEEN.
SHE LIKED SPYING
ON OTHER PEOPLE.
REGGIE THINKS THAT
GEORGE CONTINUES TO SPY
ON OTHER PEOPLE.
SHE THINKS THAT
SHE'S A GHOST.
IS THAT TRUE, REGGIE?
DO YOU THINK
YOUR SISTER, GEORGE,
IS A GHOST?
NO.
YES, YOU DO THINK
SHE'S A GHOST.
SHE THINKS
NO, I DON'T.
I'M NOT CRAZY.
I BELIEVE IN GHOSTS.
DO YOU THINK
THAT MAKES ME CRAZY?
I'D LIKE TO TALK
ABOUT MY PARENTS' DIVORCE
AND HOW THAT'S DESTROYED
MY CHILDHOOD.
I'M PAYING
$160 AN HOUR HERE, OKAY?
AND I WOULD LIKE
TO DISCUSS THE FACT
THAT REGGIE THINKS
HER SISTER IS
LIVING AMONG US.
I DON'T THINK
GEORGE IS A GHOST.
SHE'S LYING.NO, I'M NOT.
UH--I DID.
BUT I CHANGED MY MIND.
OKAY.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'VE GOT A SECRET STASH
OF LITTLE KIT KATS
IN THE OTHER ROOM,
UNDER THE COFFEE TABLE.
WANT TO GO GRAB A FEW?
SURE.
JOY...
I UNDERSTAND
YOUR FRUSTRATION, I DO,
BUT I REALLY WANT
TO ENCOURAGE YOU
TO NOT TO PUT SO MUCH
PRESSURE ON YOURSELF
OR ON REGGIE.
JUST TRY TO LET THE PROCESS
BE A LITTLE MORE ORGANIC.
I CAN'T AFFORD ORGANIC.
DANA, YOU'RE
A VERY GOOD THERAPIST,
YOU'RE A VERY SMART WOMAN,
BUT I CAN'T AFFORD
TO COME HERE.
I CAN'T EVEN AFFORD
TO PARK HERE.
OKAY, MAYBE WE CAN WORK OUT
SOME KIND OF A SLIDING SCALE.
I DON'T REALLY THINK
THAT THERAPY
IS GOING TO BRING
MY DAUGHTER BACK.
WHICH DAUGHTER
ARE YOU TRYING
TO BRING BACK?
YOU'RE A LITTLE TALLER
THAN THE OTHER
TRICK-OR-TREATERS.
CANDY BAR OR FRUIT ROLL-UP?
HOW ABOUT
A MOMENT OF YOUR TIME?
NO SALES!
I'M NOT SELLING ANYTHING.
GO AWAY.
I'M WITH, UH,
CANDY BUSTERS, INC.
I'M JUST TRYING
TO EDUCATE THE PUBLIC
ON THE PERILS OF SUGAR.
YOU PICKED
THE WRONG NIGHT!
WELL...
IT'S ONE OF THE FEW NIGHTS
PEOPLE WILL OPEN THEIR DOOR
TO STRANGERS.
QUESTION ONE...
RATE THE APPLE
AS A HALLOWEEN TREAT--
HEALTHY ALTERNATIVE
OR LIBERAL COP-OUT?
COP-OUT.
NEXT QUESTION.
LET ME GET YOUR NAME. UH...
M. FELDMAN?
JOSIE FELDMAN.
LAST QUESTION...
DID YOU KNOW CANDY
KILLS MORE PEOPLE
THAN CIGARETTES?
I DON'T BELIEVE THAT.
GOOD LUCK WITH YOUR SURVEY.
WHERE'RE YOUR FOLKS?
THEY'RE IN BARBADOS,
TRYING TO RECAPTURE
THEIR YOUTH.
WELL...
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
TAKE IN THESE NEWSPAPERS.
CRIMINALS SEE THIS,
IT'S LIKE AN INVITATION.
COME ON.
THIS NEIGHBORHOOD?
YOU HAVE A LAME JOB.
I WANT TO THANK YOU
FOR YOUR TIME.
HEY, YOU WANT TO TAKE
SOME CANDY FOR YOUR KID?
I DON'T HAVE A CHILD.COME ON.
TAKE A SNICKERS
FOR THE ROAD.
SUGAR ROCKS.
CAN I GIVE YOU
SOME ADVICE?
SURE.
ENJOY THAT CIGARETTE.
IN A WAY,
DEATH WAS KIND OF LIKE
A DOOR-TO-DOOR SALESMAN.
MOST PEOPLE
WEREN'T TOO INTERESTED
IN WHAT WE WERE SELLING.
[WHISTLING]
OR THEY JUST DIDN'T
WANT TO MAKE THAT KIND
OF LONG-TERM COMMITMENT.
[KNOCKING]
[THUD][SCREAMING]
[RUSTLING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[WHISTLING]
SO WE TRICK THEM.
YOU OKAY?
COME ON.
YOU THINK
YOU'RE TOUGH,
DON'T YOU?
WHAT?YOU THINK YOU'RE A BAD ASS
IN YOUR LITTLE GET-UP.
I COULD HAVE
PLAYED A COP, ROXY,
A COP WITH
A HEART OF GOLD.
IT'S NOT THE OUTFIT, DAISY.
BEING TOUGH IS IN HERE.
I'M TOUGH.OH, YEAH, REAL TOUGH.
YOU'RE REAL IMPOSING.
IT'S VERY EASY
FOR YOU, ROXY.
YOU ARE ARMED.
I NEED A GUN, TOO.
A GIRL NEEDS ACCESSORIES.
THE ONLY ACCESSORY I HAVE
IS MY ATTITUDE.
OH, THEN, UH,
GIVE ME YOUR GUN.
NO.PLEASE?
NO.GIVE ME THE GUN.
GIVE ME THE GUN.
GIVE ME THE GUN
JESUS CHRIST,
YOU'RE LIKE MASON.
YOU ARE NOT A COP.
AND YOU'RE NOT
A PRINCESS.
AND DON'T YOU
FUCKING FORGET IT.
THANK YOU.
OH, YOU FORGOT
TO CHARGE ME
FOR MY COFFEE.
COFFEE'S FREE FOR COPS.
SEE THE KIND
OF AN ACTRESS I AM?
IT'S JUST EFFORTLESS.
YEAH, IT WAS.
HEY, OLD MAN,
TAKE A PICTURE,
IT LASTS LONGER.
YOU SEE, ROXY?
TAKE AWAY THE UNIFORM,
YOU'RE JUST ANOTHER
PRETTY FACE.
YOU HAVE NO AUTHORITY.
AHEM.
HEY. YOU GONNA
STAND THERE GAWKING
OR AM I GOING TO HAVE
TO DRAG YOUR ASS
TO THE STATION HOUSE?
THIS IS FUN.
PERHAPS YOU DIDN'T HEAR ME,
GRANDPA, I SAID--
DAISY ADAIR.
I'M SORRY,
I DON'T KNOW WHO THAT IS.
GONE WITH THE WIND.
SHE DIED DURING THE FILMING.
YOU'RE THE SPITTING IMAGE
OF HER.
OH.
WELL, GOOD FOR ME.
I USED TO SEE MISS ADAIR
COME INTO THE STORK CLUB
EVERY NIGHT.
USUALLY WITH
A DIFFERENT GENTLEMAN.
ALL OF THEM,
OR MOST OF THEM, STARS.
WELL, I'M NOT HER.
OBVIOUSLY.
HALLOWEEN
IS ONE FUCKED-UP DAY.
GIVE ME THE GUN.
THIS LOOKS LIKE
A CHOCOLATE HOUSE,
MAYBE EVEN CARAMEL.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
THE NICE DECORATIONS
AND CARAMEL-CHOCOLATE
WRAPPER.
GET OUT
OF THE WAY! OI!
WAIT YOUR FUCKING TURN.
GET TO THE BACK!I'M NOT SCARED OF YOU.
YOU EITHER.
YOU'RE THREE-
AND-A-HALF-FEET TALL
WITH AN EARRING
AND A SASH,
SO BACK OFF.
YEAH.
OOH. WHAT SCARY CREATURES
HAVE COME TO MY DOOR?
THAT'S FOR US, THEN?
CHEERS.
UH, MASON--
DRY... ICE.
[MASON GASPING]
JESUS, THAT WAS COLD.
AND WHAT ARE YOU?
A GHOST.
AH. AND YOU?
GHOST.
GOOD JOB, GUYS.
WAY TO GO ALL OUT.
"A" FOR EFFORT.THANK YOU.
CAN WE HAVE
SOME BLOODY CANDY NOW,
OR WHAT?
MM.
GO FOR IT.
OI! GET OUT OF HERE.
COME ON, PISS OFF.
OH... HI, FRANK.
DEBRA'S IN THE ZEBRA ROOM.
OH, THAT'S JUST NOT RIGHT.
[DOORBELL RINGING]
HAPPY HALLOWEEN!
OBVIOUSLY, I'M A COUPLE
YEARS PAST
TRICK-OR-TREATING AGE,
BUT I HAD TO
COMPLIMENT YOU ON THESE
GORGEOUS DECORATIONS.
MAY I OFFER YOU
MY OREGANO-DUSTED
PUMPKIN SEEDS?
AH!
LOVELY.
YOU MUST BE MRS. CLARK.
YOU'RE A
NEIGHBORHOOD LEGEND.
YOU CAN CALL ME KATIE.
YOU DO BEAUTIFUL
WORK, KATIE.
ARE THERE ANY PROBLEMS
IN THE AREA, OFFICER?
TELL ME THOSE
AWFUL STUART BOYS
DIDN'T DEFECATE
IN MY WISHING WELL AGAIN.
NO, NO, JUST MAKING SURE
EVERYONE'S SAFE.
KIDS TODAY ARE
SO ILL-MANNERED.
HOOLIGANS.
I ADORE HALLOWEEN.
[CHUCKLES]
AND I WILL CONTINUE
TO CREATE
ELEGANT DECORATIONS
AND HEALTHY SNACKS
UNTIL THE DAY I DIE.
GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
[WHISTLING]
[DOORBELL RINGING]
I JUST CLEANED
THOSE CUPBOARDS.
PLEASE DON'T TOUCH THEM.
STOP CLEANING.
I'M HUNGRY.
HONEY, YOU KNOW
I'M GOING TO START
SHOWING THE HOUSE AGAIN.
I KNOW YOU DON'T LIKE IT.
THAT'S JUST HOW THINGS ARE.
KNOCK KNOCK.
HAPPY HALLOWEEN.
HEY, SUZANNE.
SUGAR SKULL?
OH.HMM?
I JUST HAD LUNCH.
SO HOW'RE YOU
DOING, REGGIE?
I'M FINE.
SO SORRY TO HEAR
ABOUT YOUR DOGGIE.
THANKS.
SO, THESE...
ARE FOR
DIA DE LOS MUERTOS--
DAY OF THE DEAD.
IT'S SORT OF
THE MEXICAN VERSION
OF HALLOWEEN.
EVERYONE GATHERS
AND THEY GO TO THE CEMETERY
WHERE THEIR LOVED ONES
ARE BURIED.
IT'S ACTUALLY--
IT'S THE DAY AFTER
HALLOWEEN.
SUZANNE...NO, THIS IS NOT
MORBID AT ALL, JOY.
THIS IS CELEBRATORY,
AND THERE'S SONG
AND DANCE,
AND FOOD AND MUSIC
AND CANDLES.
IT'S A REAL HOOT.
THAT'S SWEET.
THANKS FOR THE TREATS.
AND I'M HAVING
A  DIA DE LOS MUERTOSPARTY
AT MY PLACE TONIGHT.
YOU'RE BOTH INVITED
TO COME.
IT'S GOING TO BE
A VERY MELLOW VIBE.
SOME TEQUILA AND FLAN.
SOME OLDER SINGLE MEN.
WE'LL TRY TO COME BY.
YOU KNOW,
I WAS REMEMBERING
GEORGE TODAY,
IN HER LITTLE
GHOST COSTUME.
I MISS SEEING HER.
WELL,
FELIZ DIA DE LOS MUERTOS,
HONEY.
PLEASE COME.
TWO BY TWO, KIDS.
DO YOU SEE
HOW ANTONIO'S HOLDING
THE LION'S HAND?
THAT'S
THE HALLOWEEN SPIRIT.
CHARLIE, IF YOU CAN'T
KEEP YOUR HANDS OFF
THAT DINOSAUR'S TAIL,
YOU'RE GOING BACK
TO THE SHELTER EARLY.
HEY, MAN, YOU WANT
TO GET SOME CANDY?
WE CAN CATCH UP
WITH THEM LATER.
DOES, UH, OH, DOES ANYONE
HAVE TO, UH, MAKE A WEE-WEE?
TRICK OR TREAT?
HEY, YOU'RE A CUTE GUY, HUH?
THERE YOU GO.
THOSE ARE BOURBON CANDIES.
WELL, MY MOTHER
USED TO GIVE THEM TO ME
WHEN I WAS KID.
SIR...
IT'S ILLEGAL
TO GIVE ALCOHOL TO MINORS.
AW, SHIT.
I'M SORRY, I'M SORRY.
I JUST...
I'M SORRY.
I JUST HATE HOLIDAYS,
YOU KNOW?
SO GODDAMN LONELY...
WOULD YOU MIND
TELLING ME YOUR NAME, SIR?
LES...
BLANDON.
SHOULD I GO GET
THE BATHROBE?
THERE'LL BE NO ARREST
TONIGHT, MR. BLANDON.
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
THANK YOU.
COME ON, PHANTOM MAN,
LET'S HIT THE TRAILS.
[DELORES]: THERE WE GO.
KATE, DID YOU SEE
WHICH WAY--
CHARLIE! MY GOD!
YOU GAVE US A SCARE.
LOSE ONE OF YOUR GROUP,
DID YOU?
YES, AND I JUST DID
A BUDDY COUNT.[WHISTLING]
WELL, EVERYONE'S FINE.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST MOVE ON
TO THE NEXT HOUSE, THEN?
IS THERE
SOMETHING WRONG, OFFICER?
IS THERE SOME CHATTER
ON THE LINE?
NO, JUST SOME GUY
GIVING OUT BOURBON BONBONS.
LIQUOR CHOCOLATES
WERE MY GATEWAY DRUG.
THEY ARE NO JOKE.
BAG CHECK!
LET'S SEE...
OKAY. OKAY.
NO JOKE.
[WHISTLING]
OKAY...
THANK YOU, OFFICER.
COME ON, KIDS,
LET'S KEEP GOING.
ANY TIME.
THAT'S IT,
STAY CLOSE.
[WHISTLING]
THAT'S
ONE SCARY GUY.
YEAH.
THAT'S THE THING
WITH HALLOWEEN.
I WOULDN'T HAVE LOVED IT
SO MUCH IF THERE WAS NOTHING
TO BE AFRAID OF,
IF SOME OF THE HOUSES
I PEERED INTO
WEREN'T HAUNTED.
YOU ALL RIGHT
THERE, CHIEF?
YES. I AM ON A MISSION.
OI! YOU, NO.
THIS IS MY REAP,
AND THEREFORE,
MY DOORBELL RING.
WELL, THEN, HAVE AT IT.
THANK YOU.
[RINGING]
[SIGHS]
THE ADDRESS AND THE TIME
ARE THE SAME.
THAT'S KIND OF IRONIC,
ISN'T IT?
HELLO, LITTLE MAN.
TRICK OR TREAT?
WHAT ARE YOU?
[COUGHING]ME? UH, WELL, UM...
HAVE YOU EVER
HEARD OF A BRIT?
WELL, I'M A BRIT.
SO YOU'RE A LITTLE DEVIL?
YEAH.WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
BOBBY.
BOBBY, IS YOUR DAD IN?
RICHARD, OR RAYMOND, OR...
HE WENT OUT
TO GET ME SOME
COUGH MEDICINE.
ARE YOU SICK?
YEAH.
NO TRICK-OR-TREATING
THIS YEAR.
SHIT.
NOW, YOU LITTLE DEVIL...
I AM THINKING THAT MAYBE
YOUR PARENTS SOMETIMES
CALL YOU ROBERT,
ROBERT PERLIS, RIGHT?
YEAH.
KNOW WHAT I'M GOING TO DO
FOR YOU, BOBBY?
I AM GOING TO OPEN UP
MY BIG BAG HERE,
AND I'M GOING TO LET YOU
PICK ANY--ANYTHING,
ANYTHING YOU WANT,
SERIOUSLY. COME ON.
ANYTHING.
I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO
TAKE CANDY FROM
PEOPLE I DON'T KNOW.
COME ON, LITTLE MAN.
YOU KNOW ME. I'M A BRIT,
I'M NOT A MONSTER, AM I?
COME ON, CHOOSE.
NOW, THAT IS
A BLOODY GOOD CHOICE,
BOBBY, I'M TELLING YOU.
OPEN YOUR ARMS OUT.
GO ON.
THERE YOU GO.
THANKS.
HEY. COME HERE.
HAPPY HALLOWEEN.
[COUGHING]
HEY.
HOW DO YOU--
HOW DO YOU THINK
HE'S GOING TO...
HOW--
GOD, YOU DON'T THINK
HE'S GOING TO CHOKE
ON THAT CANDY
I GAVE HIM, DO YOU?
[WHISTLING]
[DOORBELL RINGING]
[JOY]: COME ON,
GEORGE, LET'S GO.
[WHISTLING]
THAT'S THE CONFUSING THING
ABOUT HALLOWEEN--
YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO BE
A LITTLE SCARED,
AND YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO OPEN YOUR DOOR
TO STRANGERS.
DOES THAT MAKE ANY SENSE?
WELL? DOES IT?
ALL RIGHT, LITTLE MAN,
COME WITH ME.
YEAH.
BETTER TO BE
JUST A LITTLE SCARED.
AHEM.
HOW DO I LOOK?EMBARRASSING.
[SIGHS]
[SNIFFS]
[SNIFFS AGAIN]
WHAT IS THAT SMELL?SHIT. PUMPKIN SEEDS.
REGGIE!
OH! CHRIST!
[SCREAMING]
PUMPKIN SEEDS.
REGGIE,
WHAT THE FUCK?
NO NEED TO
DROP THE F-BOMB.
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
I FORGOT ABOUT THEM.
I'M SORRY.
LOOK WHAT YOU DID
TO MY KITCHEN.
I MEAN,
THIS IS A DISASTER.
IT'S NOT.
REGGIE, THIS IS
UNBELIEVABLE!
WORSE THINGS
HAVE HAPPENED, MOM.
YOU ALWAYS GO CRAZY
OVER THE STUFF
THAT DOESN'T EVEN MATTER.
OKAY, THEN WHY DON'T YOU
PUT ON A COSTUME
AND COME WITH ME,
OVER TO SUZANNE'S PARTY?
I WANT TO STAY HERE.
JUST COME WITH ME.
I'LL STAY HERE
AND HAND OUT CANDY.
I DON'T THINK
THAT'S A VERY GOOD IDEA.
IT'S JUST HALLOWEEN, MOM.
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
FINE.
I'LL HAVE
MY PHONE WITH ME.
[BEEP]IT'S ON, OKAY?
OKAY.
I'LL COME BACK SOON,
AND THEN WE CAN...
WE CAN ANSWER THE DOOR
TOGETHER, OKAY?
SURE.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
IT'LL BE A HOOT.
I DON'T REMEMBER
EVERY SINGLE MOMENT
ABOUT BEING A KID...
BUT I SURE
REMEMBER HALLOWEEN.
THE STUFF
THAT SENT MY HEART RACING
HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH
GHOULS OR GOBLINS
OR WITCHES
OR EVEN GHOSTS.
THE STUFF THAT SCARED ME
WAS WHAT WAS LURKING BEHIND
ALL THOSE CLOSED DOORS,
ALL THOSE SECRETS
HIDING IN THE DARK...
[♪♪]
YOU REALLY WANT TO KNOW
HOW TO SCARE THE CRAP
OUT OF YOURSELF?
SOME HALLOWEEN NIGHT,
GO RING THE WRONG DOORBELL.
[DOORBELL RINGING]
YES?
WHY DON'T YOU GIVE OUT CANDY
LIKE A NORMAL PERSON?
WELL, YOUNG LADY,
I LEFT A BOWL,
AND YOU KICKED IT OVER.
[JOY]: COME ON,
GEORGE, LET'S GO!
GEORGIA, COME ON!
I HAVE TO GO.
ALL RIGHT.
BUT COME BACK
NEXT YEAR.
IF MOST PEOPLE KNEW
HOW MANY TIMES
THEY BRUSHED BY DEATH,
THEY'D PROBABLY STAY INSIDE
FOR THE REST OF THEIR LIVES.
OR AT LEAST THEY WOULDN'T
KNOCK ON THIS DARK DOOR.
TRICK OR TREAT.
I DON'T HAVE ANY CANDY.
I SEE YOUR CANDY
RIGHT THERE.
I KNOW YOU.
IT'S DONE.
IT'S ALL OVER.
WHO ARE YOU?
NOBODY
YOU WANT TO KNOW.
I DIDN'T KNOW
HOW HE WAS GOING TO DIE.
AND TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
I REALLY DIDN'T GIVE A SHIT.
SOME OF THE DEAD
ARE JUST BETTER LEFT
FORGOTTEN.
REGGIE, WE CAN GO
BACK TO THE PARTY,
WE CAN GO HOME...
I'LL DO
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
I AM JUST
NOT COMFORTABLE...
HERE.
IT'S TOO DISTURBING.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE
DISTURBING.
IT'S HALLOWEEN
IN A GRAVEYARD.
IT'S THE DAY
OF THE DEAD.
YOU KNOW, REGGIE,
ACTUALLY,
DIA DE LOS MUERTOS
IS TOMORROW.
SUZANNE SAID
IT'S THE ONE DAY
WHEN SPIRITS
VISIT THE EARTH.
YEAH, AND THAT ONE DAY
IS ACTUALLY TOMORROW,
AS IN THE DAYTIME, HMM?
AND SUZANNE
SMOKES A LOT OF POT.
LET'S GO HOME.
YOU DIDN'T EVEN
GO TRICK-OR-TREATING
THIS YEAR.
THAT MAKES ME SAD.
I'M DONE WITH IT.
IS IT BECAUSE GEORGE
ALWAYS USED TO TAKE YOU
TRICK-OR-TREATING?
AND IGNORED ME.
COME HERE.
COME KEEP
YOUR MOTHER WARM.
FUCKING BULLSHIT.
I DON'T LIKE
ALMONDS AND COCONUT
IN MY CHOCOLATE.
I DO.
MAKE ME AN OFFER.
UH, MILK DUDS
AND A CANDY BAR
TO BE NAMED LATER?
OKAY.
BLACK LICORICE--
TOTALLY GROSS.
WHO WANTS TO TRADE?
FINE.
BE THAT WAY.
[GROWLS]
HEY, RUBE, SURE
YOU DON'T WANT ANYTHING?
HALLOWEEN'S FOR KIDS.
YOU GUYS HAVE IT.
I HAVE TO ADMIT, MASON,
THIS IS
AN IMPRESSIVE HAUL.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, DAISY.
YOU MUST'VE
REALLY WORKED HARD.
YOU DON'T KNOW.
ANYWAY, THANKS.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
COME ON, RUBE.
I KNOW
YOU LOVE SWEETS.
HAVE SOMETHING.
I WOULDN'T MIND
A LITTLE PEANUT
BRITTLE, PEANUT.
THAT'S NOT WHO I AM ANYMORE,
I'M NOT THAT GIRL.
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
WELL, HAPPY HALLOWEEN
ANYWAY...
PEANUT.
WELL, IT'S NOT
HALLOWEEN ANYMORE.
IT'S TOMORROW.
ALL SAINTS' DAY.
IS THAT
A SPECIAL ONE, TOO?
DO I HAVE TO WEAR A MASK?
LEGEND HAS IT THAT SPIRITS
GATHER IN GRAVEYARDS
ON ALL SAINTS' DAY.
THAT'S WHERE
THEY HONOR THE DEAD.
HOW WILL YOU
BE SPENDING IT?
IN A GRAVEYARD.
GOOD NIGHT, GUYS.
BYE.
[SNARLING]
[GROWLING]
I ALWAYS THOUGHT
I LOVED HALLOWEEN
BECAUSE I GOT TO LOOK BEHIND
ALL THOSE CLOSED DOORS,
BUT NOW I SEE THAT IT'S
BECAUSE I WAS PAINTED
WITH SOMETHING DARKER...
THAT I WAS MEANT
TO SEE THE DARK,
AND THROUGH THE DARK...
I'M NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE HERE...
BUT I AM.
I DON'T KNOW
IF I'M SUPPOSED TO
WATCH OVER THEM,
OR JUST HAUNT THEM.
EITHER WAY, I'D BE LYING
IF I SAID I WASN'T
HAVING FUN.
I'D BE LYING IF I SAID
I DIDN'T WANT TO BE HERE...
WALKING THROUGH A GRAVEYARD
THE DAY AFTER HALLOWEEN,
ON A QUIET AND BEAUTIFUL
NOVEMBER MORNING...
IT'S NOT SO BAD...
BEING DEAD LIKE ME.