You folks have a nice day.
I do not like him.
Don't you want to just slap
that smile right off his face?
[GRUNTS]
He's dead.
Darling,
there's no post-it.
[GROWLS]
[SCREECHING]
What the fuck
was that?
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
MAN: Forward, hut!
GEORGE:
When I was alive,
I never bought
the whole straighten-up
and fly-right routine.
I hated being told
what to do,
so it's pretty strange
that now my job
is to give everyone else
their marching orders.
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
GEORGE:  Sure, I wanted to be
a superhero when I was a kid,
but only the guy superheroes
got cool costumes...
Massive capes
and scary masks and stuff.
All Wonder Woman got
were hooker boots
and a bathing suit.
What the fuck
was that about?
♪ My mom's a whore,
my dad likes porn
ALL:
♪ My mom's a whore,
my dad likes porn
♪ My sister blows
my brother's horn
ALL:
♪ My sister blows
my brother's horn ♪
GEORGE:
Ah, the gentle art of poetry.
MAN: All right, let's go.
Move it, move it, move it!
Pick up your feet!
Let's go, move it!
Hit that wall, up and over,
up and over.
Do you want to fly with
the brotherhood of the eagles,
or do you want
to slither with the worms?
Sir, I want to fly
with the eagles, sir.
Then let me see you get
up and over that wall,
cadet. Now!
Sir, I have to go
to the bathroom, sir.
I'll bet you do,
Monteleone.
The idea of that wall
is scaring
the piss out of you.
No, sir. No fear, sir.
We've never had a girl
scale that wall
before, Monteleone,
I'm sure we never will.
Sir, I will
scale the wall, sir!
You show these boys
you mean business.
Dismissed!
[MEN LAUGHING]
Knock it off, ladies.
[MONTELEONE COUGHING]
[RETCHING]
I'm not scared of heights.
I just have to
catch my breath.
I'm going to be
the first girl
over that wall.
[CHUCKLES]
Even if it kills you, huh?
Who the hell are you?
I'm just taking a tour.
I think I might
want to enlist.
You don't enlist,
you enroll.
Mmm.Anyway, you should.
It changed my life.
You have no idea.
Permission to kick
some ass now, sir!
GEORGE:
She's feisty, that one.
I'm kind of rooting for her.
Move it, girly.
Up and over that wall, now!
Move it, move it!
[GRUNTS]Move it!
GEORGE:
Come on. Here we go.
You can do it.
[GRUNTS]
GEORGE:  Ouch!
Come on, pick yourself up.
Let's go. You can do it.[LAUGHS]
[PANTING]
[GROWLING]
[LAUGHING TRIUMPHANTLY]
I knew you could do it.
[WHOOPING]
Wow, good for you.MONTELEONE: Yeah!
First girl on
top of this wall!
GEORGE:  And not so good.
Did you kill me?
No, I took your
soul before you died.
Think of me as one of
Death's little lieutenants.
So, you're dead, too?
Dead and buried.
So how did you end up
in this place?
You burn your
parents' house down?
I had to ace four tests
to get in here.
I was selected.
Well, I was selected, too.
Why?
I don't know.
So, do you have
any superpowers?
Can you fly?
No. No flying,
no leaping of buildings,
no climbing walls.
But we can drink
as much tequila
as we want
without
getting hung over.
That's pretty cool.
MASON:
All right, one more time.
What is the story?
I broke up with Ray.
[WHISPERS] That's our story.
But I hit him on the head
with a blunt object.
Yeah, our story is
I dumped him.
I dumped him,
in your backyard,
in a shallow grave.
Is that what you
want me to tell Rube?
It's fine.
When you have to lie,
you have to remember shit,
and I really,
really hate remembering shit.
The key to
successful lying is telling
a simple yet
elegant story, all right?
It's like
a little black dress,
short, simple,
classic, unforgettable.
Hmm. Bowling!
I'll say I went bowling
at the weekend
when I was meant
to be killing Ray.
That is neither
simple nor elegant.
All right?
This is not a joke.
You killed a man.
It was self-defense.
The first blow to the head
was self-defense.
The three other
blows after that
was probably a little
bit murderous, but...
Are you trying to be funny?
Yeah. No.
I don't know.
Sure. Why not?
I haven't slept a wink
since it happened.
I am totally on edge.
My nerves are totally fried.
Oh, my God.
Why didn't you say
something earlier?
I reaped this junkie
housewife last week,
and I hit the mother lode.
Look, Diazepam, Lorazepam.
This is
a gorilla tranquilizer.
They are really fabulous.
Mason! I don't want
to be numb right now.
We need to deal with this.
Coffee?
Yes, please,
and keep it coming, Kiffany.
Hello, Kiffany.
Did you have a good weekend?
I had a brilliant weekend.
I went bowling.
I'm a big bowler, I am.
A great bowler.
I was rolling,
I was throwing,
pins were flying
fucking everywhere,
everywhere, they were.
[STAMMERING]
I threw a...
I bowled a 360.
[GROANS]
Good for you.
You've wound me up now.
You're going?
Please don't go.
Don't be clingy.
It's unattractive.
I'm going to powder my nose.
CLANCY: Good morning.Yes, it is.
Oh, Dad! Ew!
How are your pancakes?
I should have
gotten waffles.
Reggie, don't drink coffee.
I like it. Mom lets me.
You know who used to
really love coffee?
Two sugars and
a little milk.
You sure you're
going to be okay
after school?
Yes.
Because I can call your mom
and have her come home early.
Don't.Or I can call
the babysitter.
Alison Alpert has
been staying home alone
since the fifth grade.
I think I should
call your mom and ask.
She won't care, believe me.
Anything else
for you today?
Just the check, please.Okay.
Thank you.
Good morning.RUBE: Good morning.
How's the coffee today?
A little weak.
Are you sitting or
just standing guard?
We're moving.
You love this booth.
Well, call me crazy,
I need a little
natural light today.
Over by the window.
Come on, march.
Where's Daisy?
I don't know.
How am I
supposed to know that?
How am I to
know everything?
I can't remember everything.
I actually can't
remember anything.
How should I know?
Back the fuck up, Roxy.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Where is she?
Bathroom.
You hitting
the bottle already?
Coffee.
Irish?
I'm English.
So what's the deal
with Daisy and this Ray guy?
That dead and buried?
God damn it.
It's my favorite
fucking pants, my shirt.
What the fuck is
the matter with you?
I'm terribly, terribly sorry.
Is that necessary?
Saliva has enzymes,
breaks this shit down.
We're over here.
Attagirl.
How'd the early reap go, huh?
Good. Militant. Depressing.
Another young one?
Yeah. Strong and motivated.
Reaping a winner
makes me feel
like a loser.
I mean, I'm not a loser,
I'm just, you know,
alone and dead.
Did anyone here ever
serve in the military?
No, nobody here did.
I think Daisy
serviced the army.[LAUGHS]
I don't care for
that kind of joke.
You are that kind of joke.
And since when are
you Daisy's defender?
Since always.
Where is Daisy, anyway?
She's in some serious,
fucking trouble.
She didn't do it.Do what?
She didn't do that
what you said she did.
Well, somebody
tracked mud in the house
and it wasn't me.
And a good morning
to you all.
Yes, it's a jolly
good day, isn't it?
Yeah.
Give her your chair.
What the jolly hell
is up with you two?
All right, that's enough.
I was bowling, all weekend.
I'm in a bowling league.
Did you know that?
I'm in a bowling league,
and you can ask my
fucking friend, Lester.
Why would I do that?
For you.
You.
And for you.
The Post-it is purple.
ROXY: I have multiples.
What's that about?
Affirmative action.
Hardy-har-har.
You know,
you better hope coffee
comes out of these pants.
These I value
a little bit more than you,
my friend.
My Post-it is purple.
[EXCLAIMS]
You're on my list, Mason.
What list? What...
What list?
GEORGE: My reap this morning
asked me what I did on my
last day on Earth.
My answer was so
fucking boring,
I could have died.
Again.
Why? What was it?I filed.
Isn't that what you do now?
If I had known it was
my last day on Earth,
I would have...
I have no idea.
Would you have
gotten really drunk
and high?
No.
I would have found that bitch
that killed me,
and I would have...
Killed her?
Punished her. Big time.
DAISY: I would've
gotten engaged.
I always wanted
someone to slip
a pretty little
diamond ring on my finger.
I've got a purple Post-it.
Purple was my favorite color
when I was a kid.
Purple is the color
of royalty and extravagance.
Have you had a purple Post-it?
Have you guys
ever had a purple...
Just ask Rube about it.I will.
Don't.I won't.
GEORGE: Daisy,
you tracked mud in the house.
What were you doing
that was so muddy?
Bowling!
I'll just clean it up.
I'm leaving, okay?
There's no milk left.
I've got a purple Post-it.
GEORGE:
Nothing lasts forever.
This was a lesson
I learned over and over again.
At Happy Time,
at a temp agency,
people definitely come and go.
In fact, most days,
you can't swing a dead cat
without hitting
a fucking good-bye party.
Another office farewell,
Delores?
Yeah.
Can you believe Brian
is leaving us already?
Only the good
go so quickly.
You don't have to tell me.
[ALL EXCLAIMING]
MISTY: Nice save, Millie.
Yeah, that could've
been ugly.
Yeah,  The Attack of
the Killer Pinata.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Misty, can you get me
my stepladder, pumpkin?Mmm-hmm.
GEORGE:  Pumpkin?
She's your pumpkin?
Nice hustle, Misty.
Team player.
So, Millie, can you help me
with the party prep?
I know it's not
really your thing,
but that bean dip isn't
going to layer itself.
Delores, don't you think
just a good hearty handshake
and "Get out"
would be good enough?
Millie, Brian is hanging up
his Happy Time hat
and riding off into
the sunset,
and I expect the appropriate
show of emotion.
I'm sorry, Delores.
I just can't get it
up for every
Tom, Dick and Brian
who decide to move on.
Hey, that's not
a very nice thing to say.
Well,
if it makes a difference,
I'm really gonna miss you.
Uh, Misty,
that's not Brian.
Oh, [LAUGHS] sorry.
Shame on you, Ron.
I'm Brian,
and I'm really going
to miss you, too, Misty.
Thank you.
Look, Millie,
I really need your help.
I've got a lunch date,
and I need to get
things ready quickly,
so can you pretend to care?
What kind of lunch date?
Love.com.
I'm back online, Millie.
His name is Lionel.
Smart, driven,
types like a jackal.
Well, I'm really
happy for you, Delores.
I just don't want
to look back one day
and say "What if?"
No.
GEORGE:
As in, what if you went out
to lunch one day
and never came back?
It was almost enough
to make you
understand the stupid fuss
over good-bye parties.
Almost.
ALL: Go, Sea Turtles!
Why am I here with you?
Hold this.
Oh, what,
so I'm a coffee
bloody table?
If I say so.
What is this, anyway?
Cricket, tennis, football?
What are you people, frogs?
MAN: We're Sea Turtles!
ALL: Sea Turtles! Yeah!
Fucking hell!
Give them a little rah-rah-rah
while I reap, reap, reap.
Wait here.
Sea turtles freak me out.
Me, too.
A friend of mine
was swimming across
this creek
and got his balls snapped off
by a sea turtle.
Sea creatures don't
swim in the creek.
They swim in the sea.
Well, these are scary
little fuckers, dude.
Devious.
The interesting
part of that story
is that your friend
got his nuts clamped by
a creature, a sea creature.
I drive better
when I'm high.
I'll bet you do.
[SNARLING]
Bye.
[GRUNTS]
Hey, you never
told me what happened
to Daisy and Ray.
Like, post mortem.
Finished, ended, period.
I thought she was in love.
Go, Sea Turtles.
Yeah, you kill them.
She dumped him.
Why?She's secretly
in love with me.
Now, that I do not follow.
[GRUNTS]
Go, Turtles.
Snap!
[WHOOPING]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO]
What do you want to do today?
We're all alone.
You know what this means.
Rocky Road, your favorite.[WHIMPERING]
[KNOCKING]CLAIRE: Reggie.
[BARKING]J.D., shh.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
CLAIRE:
Reggie, can you open up?
Hi, Mrs. Henican.
Hi. Call me Claire.
Why?
Well, 'cause I
asked you to, dear.
I didn't see
your mom come home,
and I heard the music.
I just wondered if
everything was all right.
She's visiting my grandma,
and I'm allowed to be alone.
She'll be home tonight.
Oh, no.
Should he be eating that?
Dogs don't do
well with chocolate.
It's low fat.
Sweetheart, I know how
painful divorce can be,
so if you ever feel isolated,
you knock on my door.
Just don't take
my toilet seat.
Can you close
the gate behind you
so J.D. doesn't get out?
Are you sure you want
to let him eat that?
It's very bad for dogs.
Thanks for
stopping by, Claire.
GEORGE:
What kind of food is this?
DELORES: Frontier.
I was up all night simmering
these franks and beans.
Had a real scare with Murray
and a teeny piece of weenie.
Had to Heimlich
the poor guy.
DELORES:
Crystal, how are the beans?
Great.
Brian!Millie.
Brian, it's
supposed to be a surprise.
Get out.
[CHUCKLES] Right.
Sorry, Delores.
I just wanted
to say thank you.
You know, when...
When I left Pizza Hut,
all they gave me
was a small
Meat Lovers Supreme
and my nametag.
This means so much to me.
Okay, I'm gonna...
He's so full of shit.
And why so cynical?
Because he's a turd.
[FARTING]
What do you
have against Brian?
Because when I
first met him, he...
Here's how he shook my hand.
Here,
hold out your hand, Crystal.
Pretend you're me.
Exactly.
Ever since then,
I haven't trusted him.
And you know what they say
about people with
weak handshakes?
Small gloves?Don't trust them.
You know what, Millie?
People have one chance
to make a first impression
and one chance
to make a last.
The way we say goodbye
to people matters.
People remember
their last day,
and Brian's gonna remember his
and you can be
a part of it or not.
Clammy handshakes,
give me the fucking creeps.
Nice, Crystal.
Dry, strong,
trustworthy, loyal.
What is on your hand?
Motor oil? Peanut butter?
That is one filthy paw.
Come on, it's only blood.
It's not like it's mine.
Please read it, Kiffany.
Kiffany.
Kiffany, please read it,
read it, Kiffany.
No.
George says that
you're a palm reader.
You know, she said
that you're...
[WHISPERING] Psychotic.
I'm not psychic.
I think you are.
I have tables.
I'll give you 10 bucks.
You only have
two in your pocket.
Wow.
Is it my last day?
If I don't take
care of my customers,
it's going to be mine.
On your last day on Earth,
they say you'll
see a crescent moon
in the daylight.
You see a crescent moon?No.
All I see is
the same old overcast sky.
Yeah.
[BANGING ON DOOR]
ROXY: Open up! Police.
Roxy.
Don't do that.
To what do I owe
the forced entry?
Police business.
That is quite
an impressive guy
you were seeing.
Fraud, assault, bad haircut.
Yeah, so he was a bad guy.
He's gone. Who cares?
The people on his job care.
They reported him missing.
Well, then he's no
longer a threat to me.
I never said he was.
I'm done with him.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to catch up
on my magazine, so...
Looks like dried blood.
We inherited this
house from Mason
and he inherited it
from a dead woman,
so that must have
been where she died.
Yeah, maybe.
You leave it
there long enough,
it'll last forever.
That rug's been
there a long time, Roxy.
Haven't we all?
See you around.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
It's time.
Who would like to tell Brian
there's a "package" for him?
I would.
I would love to tell
Brian there's a package
waiting for him to unwrap.
Millie, you tell him.
GEORGE:  I don't know
why I had such a big
bug up my ass
about
Brian's farewell party.
Maybe it's because
I was regretting
my own last day.
Maybe it's because
he was stealing
Delores' wallet.
I was just looking
for a pen.
In Delores' wallet?
Look, a pterodactyl!
GEORGE:  Please tell me
I didn't just fall for that.
[WESTERN MUSIC PLAYING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Man down!
Millie! What is going on?
Why don't you ask Brian?
[GROANS]
She attacked me.
He was trying to
steal your wallet.
No, no, I wasn't.
Have you ever
heard the sound of
a rib cracking, Brian?
It sounds real cool!
I stole it. I stole it.
[GAGS]
Delores was trying
to do something nice for you,
and you
took advantage of her.[GROANS]
[PANTING]
I'm diabetic.[ALL GASP]
So the hell what?
I don't know.
May I do
the honors, Delores?
Please,
but watch the language.
Get the F out
before I kick
your F-ing A again.
[GRUNTS]
[GEORGE SIGHS]
You know, Delores,
you think you know someone...
I know.[ELEVATOR DINGS]
I had no idea he
was a diabetic.
I would have got
him a special cake.
[J.D. WHIMPERING]
REGGIE:
Mom's gonna to be so pissed.
Yeah, too much ice cream.
[VOMITING]
Oh, J.D.!
I'm going to be
in so much trouble.
Come on,
you're going outside.
Now.
[PEOPLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
WOMAN 1: Honey, handcuffs.
WOMAN 2: How much?
I'm not going to let that go
for any less than $20.
That's
sentimental value, that is.
It really is,
it means a lot to me.
All right, $15.
Bloody hell,
you drive a hard bargain.
$10, hand it over.
And smile once in a while.
Whoo! Come on, you lovely
people, get your bargains,
everything must go.
Hello, Father.Hello.
How much for
the incense burner?
For you, Father,
that incense burner, $5.
May the Lord bake with you.
Would you bless me?
I don't think so.
That seems fair.
WOMAN: Excuse me.
Coming, madam.
Hello.
So, what are these holes?
Oh, this is a really,
really bloody
funny story, right.
They're actually
gunshot wounds and...
Actually, that's really sad.
I've got a really
good deal for you.
I'm going to give you
all this set for $50
and, bargain of the century,
I'm going to throw in...
Ta-da! The Kitchen Guillotine.
Now, it slices, it dices,
it'll cut your bloody
hand off, it will. Yeah?
[CHUCKLES POLITELY]
No? Come on.
[CAR TIRES SCREECHING]If it makes you
feel any better,
this bloke who was murdered
on this mattress was
really lovely, he was.
What is this?
What are you doing?
Uh, having a lawn sale.
It's my lawn.
Since when was
it illegal to have
a lawn sale
on somebody else's lawn?
Oh, since forever.
Really?
I'll give you
the whole lot for $250.
I am calling the police.
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
I don't need this shit.
Well, cake looked good.
What kind was it?
German chocolate.
They had
coconut in Dodge City?
I'm on a budget, Millie.
And German Chocolate
is more than that diabetic
P-R-I-C-K deserved.
At least he
didn't get the money.
It's not about the money.
It just wasn't the goodbye
that I had in mind
when Murray and I
were up slaving over
this frosting last night.
One of these days,
I'm gonna bake
a cake with your name on it.
Oh, I don't know.
I can't bear to
think about it.
GEORGE:
I was beginning
to understand
why we mark every
coming and going
with a party.
We do it to sugarcoat
the whole "moving on" thing.
I mean,
why say an actual goodbye
to someone
when it's so much easier
to just eat cake?
Hello.
What are you doing here?
And how did you get cake?
Crystal.
Hello.
Why are you here?
I came to see
your lovely face.
I have work to do, Mason.
What do you need? Money?
Of course, I need money,
but that's not why I'm here.
For what? Drugs? Booze?
Drugs and booze?
No, actually, I want...
Seriously, Mason,
you're not supposed
to be here, so, go away!
God.
Actually, you know what?
I'm gonna stay.
And I want to say
something to you,
and you've got
to listen, please.
You know,
this morning, when you said
you spent your
last day on Earth,
your very, very last
day on Earth stapling?
Filing.
My God, that's even worse.
You said you
regretted it, didn't you?
Yeah, of course.
Who gives a shit?
By God, I give a shit.
Rube tells us to
be on the periphery,
to keep away from things,
keep our distance
from life, our family.
Yeah?
God, it is nonsense.
You get close.
George,
you get close to everybody
that ever meant
anything to you.
Have you been drinking?
Of course,
I've bloody been drinking,
and it's last call.
And you've got to...
You've got to drink
up while you still can.
I really love you, Georgie.
It's going to be all right.
Come on, let's go for a ride.
GEORGE:  I don't exactly know
what Mason was talking about,
why he said I should
get close to people,
why he told me he loved me.
Maybe it was just
the booze talking.
In vino veritas.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
I just knew it was time
to check in with my old life.
J.D.!
GEORGE:  I knew it
was time to go home.
Where are you?
Here, boy!
It's time to come home.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
I'm not here.
MASON: Well, that's strange,
because I can hear
your voice, my darling.
[SIGHS]
You can't hear me.
You're hearing
voices in your head.
That, my dear,
is so bloody true
it's scary.
Not today, Mason.
Well, today is
the day it has to be,
I'm afraid.
Can I have a drink? Thanks.
Roxy knows about Ray.
Shit.
How the hell does
she know?
She's smart.
I think she knows something.
I think someone
knows something.
I don't bloody care.
The deed is done.
You should care, Mason.
It's a death
without a Post-it.
We've let loose
some kind of evil.
All right, Daisy.
[MASON MOANING]
Look at me.
I did it, and you didn't.
Well, someone's
going to pay.
You are so
beautiful to look at.
And unlucky to know.
That's an engagement ring.
Yeah.
You wanted one,
so I got it for you.
You wanted to put it
on your little finger
on your last day,
so, here it is.
Are you trying
to humiliate me?
No.
Never.
It's a token, Daisy.
It's a token from me,
from my heart to you.
You.
There's something permanent
in this bloody world.
Mason, I'm not this girl.
I won't fall in love.
I won't get married.
I won't grow old
with someone.
Not with you or anyone.
So, I don't want your ring.
And I will never,
ever take it back.
[SNIFFLES]
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Please go.
J.D.!
GEORGE:  I would never grow up,
and I would never get old.
But my sister,
she was changing.
Growing taller, moving on.
And it was
kind of comforting.
Death may have found me,
but she seemed okay.
Hey, Charlie.
Toilet seat girl.
Funny.
What are you doing here?
You know, my job.
No.
Look, I'll give you money.
Come on,
kid, what do you want?
You can't do this.
Too late.
[DOG BARKING]
J.D.
GEORGE:
I shouldn't have come here.
This was all my fault.
Well, this is it, then.
My dog died.
You don't have a dog.
My family's dog died.
You don't have a family.
Oh, shut up, Daisy.
It's just...
It's that kind of day.
So your dog died.
I don't even know
why I went back home.
Because Mason told me to.
You shouldn't listen to Mason.
Mason doesn't know anything.
It's all my fault.
I don't think it is.
Well, then,
whose fault is it?
Probably mine.
[SCREECHES]
What is that?Go away!
Ray, go away!
Daisy,
why is there a graveling?
Mason killed Ray.
So, Mason had his Post-it?
No one had a Post-it.
There was no Post-it,
and bad things
have been happening today,
and it's all my fault.
So, I'm sorry
about your dog, babe.
It's my fault.
[REGGIE SNIFFLES]
What can I do
for you, sweetie?
Nothing.
How about some ice cream?
No. I want Mom.
She'll be back soon.
She's gonna kill me.
No one's killing anyone.
It wasn't your
fault, sweetie.
It's Claire's fault.
[SNIFFLES]
Claire from next door?
She left the gate open.
I'm gonna kill her.
Hey there, stranger.Hello.
Can I interest you in
the catch of the day?
No, thank you. [CHUCKLES]
But this smells good, though,
whatever this is.
Well, have a seat.
I've got lots of room.
I've got lots of food.
It's the second
rule in backpacking,
that you always bring
enough for a friend.
Oh, yeah?
What's the first rule?
That you make a friend.
I'm Brett Tanenbaum.
I'm Mason.
Very nice to meet you.
Well, Mason,
the house specialty tonight
is chicken noodle soup, and...
Well, that's it.
[LAUGHS] Looks good.
Are you coming
or are you going?
I'm not sure.
Yeah.
Sometimes, all this beauty
does that to me, too.
The great outdoors has a way
of scrambling your brain.
Brett,
I've done most of my brain
scrambling indoors, actually.
[COYOTE HOWLING]
Are you scared
of wild animals?
No.
I'm not really
scared of anything.
You should be.
[EXCLAIMS]
Delicious.
No. Thank you.
Oh, lovely.
So you're not
scared of anything?
Well, I won't go
swimming once it's dark.
That's kind of spooky.
Yeah, spooky, man.
[CHUCKLES] Spooky.
What if I were to
tell you this was your
last day on Earth?
What would you say?
Well, I would say that,
that's a very
strange question.
What would you say?
Well,
I would say that I would sit
under the wide open sky,
and I would fish,
and I would go for a swim
before it got dark,
which is exactly
what I'm doing today.
It's your last day on Earth.
Do you wanna tell me
what the hell
you're talking about?
It's my last day, too.
What can I get
you this evening?
I'll have a Scotch.
Wish I could, sweetheart.
Coffee then, please.
I don't know how you do it.
Do what?Your job.
The scrawny one?
He committed
a lewd act today.
On who?
A perfectly
innocent coconut cake.
I'll take care of it.
Well, you know what they say,
you don't get to
pick your family.
No.
There's your first initial,
your last name,
the place, and the time.
That's all we get.
That's not a lot to go on.
No, it isn't.
Death has a way of
pointing things
out quite simply.
Because a purple
Post-it note tells me
I'm gonna die?
No, I'm sorry,
I can't believe that.
I don't understand this,
but they're not
usually purple.
This is the first
one I've ever seen.
They're usually yellow.
And what do you
think that means?
Fucked if I know.
But one thing
I'm pretty sure of
is that you're
going to die tonight,
and I'm so sorry.
So how am I gonna die?
Wild animals,
hunter, bad aim.
I mean, how am I gonna die?
With grace, I suspect.
What did you just do?
Whatever happens to
you tonight, mate,
you will not feel a thing,
so don't be afraid.
I'm not afraid.
I just don't know
what to hope for.
[WHISPERING]
Hope for another shot at it.
A chance to do it
all fucking unafraid.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[SIGHS]
I'm gonna go for a swim.
So what's
the deal with this guy?
You think he's gone?
He's gone. Trust me.
I do not mind saying
that I did not like this guy.
I'm thinking
you'll never have
to see him again.
Never have to
see who again?
Ray.
He was last seen in Portland.
Portland?
So you're off the hook,
aren't you, Daisy?
What does that mean?
No more Ray to worry about.
Yeah, that's right.
No more Ray.
Morning.
[GROANS SOFTLY]
Why the face?
GEORGE: Leave me alone.
Her family dog died.
Oh, I'm sorry.Thanks.
Well, I'd ask you how
you know that but...
But you won't.
Well, maybe I'll
ask you tomorrow.
Tomorrow.
Well, you look like
you're at death's door.
How'd your reap go?
Swimmingly.
Lake, lightning...
[IMITATING THUNDER]
Man, gone in an instant.
Better him than you.
Do you really think so?
I do.
I've got
a question to ask you.
Shoot.
You gave me
a purple Post-it.
That's not a question.
Why did you give
me a purple Post-it?
They were out of
yellow at Office Hut.
For you.
You.
Have fun, kiddies.
You should thank Roxy.
Really? Why?Just thank her.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Would you give me
a ride to my reap?
Sure, but you have
to sit in the back.
Okay.
I'll talk to you.
[GROANING]
Could you buy me a coffee,
please?
I've got no money.
I haven't got anything.
No problem.
I have nowhere to stay.
I have no idea how
long I'll be staying.
I know.
[SNIGGERING]
GEORGE:  So maybe we don't know
what the exact sign will be
that tells us
we're moving on,
but there will be
a last reap.
"Stop noticing."
That's what Rube says.
That's how you survive.
But Mason's right.
What Rube says is bullshit.
You should get
close to everything
you care about.
Things come and go.
People come and go.
And maybe some of us
learn to stop caring
about it.
But I keep
reaching out,
even though my hand keeps
getting slapped away.
When my sister was little,
she used to close her eyes
every time she wanted to hide.
She thought that
made her disappear.
[DOORBELL RINGING]
When you get older,
you learn that
closing your eyes
just makes it darker.
[CROAKING]
You have to face everything,
even death,
if you wanna grow up.
Hello, Mr. Frog.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]