[♪♪]
[GEORGE]  I KNOW THERE ARE
BILLIONS OF STARS IN THE SKY,
AND THEY'RE ALL TWINKLING.
I WONDER WHAT MAKES ONE STAR
MORE IMPORTANT THAN ANOTHER?
I MEAN, WHY DOES ONE STAR
BECOME PART OF THE BIG DIPPER,
AND ANOTHER JUST FLAME OUT?
WOW.
SEE THAT
SHOOTING STAR?
MY NAME'S VANCE.
YOU TOLD ME THAT
ALREADY.
RIGHT.
I'M JUST
A LITTLE NERVOUS TONIGHT.
YOU SHOULD BE.
IS THAT ME?
SHIT!
I ONLY TOOK
ONE HIT.
HOW STUPID
IS THAT?
WELL, THEY DON'T CALL IT
DOPE FOR NOTHING.
SO...
WHAT HAPPENS NEXT?
DO I GO UP THERE?
YOU'RE ASKING
THE WRONG GIRL.
SOME PEOPLE BELIEVE
THERE'S SOMETHING BIGGER
OUT THERE...
THAT THERE'S SOMETHING
PROTECTING US,
WATCHING OVER US AS WE CHANGE.
[FOOTSTEPS]
I GUESS IT'S COMFORTING
TO THINK THAT SOMEONE
IS LOOKING IN ON US.
[THUMP]
REGGIE.
REGGIE, LET'S GO.
COME ON, COME ON.
HURRY UP.
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
JUST BE QUIET.
JUST GET IN THE CAR.
MORNING!
SORRY. WE--WE WAKE YOU UP?
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING ON MY HOUSE?
DON'T MIND HER, HANK.
LAST TO RISE,
FIRST TO WORRY.
MOTHER!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
JOY, DEAR, DID YOU
HONESTLY THINK
THAT I WAS JUST GOING
TO WRITE YOU A CHECK
FOR FIXING THIS ROOF
WITHOUT LOOKING
AT IT MYSELF FIRST?
I ALWAYS WARNED YOU
THIS HOUSE
IS IN LOUSY SHAPE.
NO, YOU ACTUALLY USED TO
SAY THAT ABOUT MY MARRIAGE.
YOU SEE?
RIGHT ON BOTH COUNTS.
HI, REGGIE!
HI, GRANDMA.
COME ON--
HANK, WOULD YOU MIND
PUTTING THE BAGS
OVER THERE?
SURE.THANKS.
WELL...
THAT MAN HAS
THE MOST AMAZING
HINDQUARTERS.
[GIGGLING]
REGGIE, YOU NEED TO, UH,
GO GET READY FOR SCHOOL.
OH, RELAX, JOY.
WE'RE ALL WOMEN HERE.
I MEAN IT, REGGIE.
CLANCY HAD SUCH A FLAT ASS.
YOU REALLY CAN'T TRUST
A MAN WITH A FLAT ASS.
MOM.NOTHING
TO HOLD ON TO.
YOU KNOW WHO HAS
THE BEST ASS?
DEREK JETER.
TCH-KA, TCH-KA, TCH-KA.
YOU--YOU--THIS--
YOU CAN'T BE HERE.
THE THING IS, JOY,
I AM HERE.
I SHOULD'VE
BEEN HERE BEFORE,
BUT I WAS RESPECTING
YOUR WISHES.
SO, AT THE END OF THE DAY,
WHAT HAS THAT ACCOMPLISHED?
YOU NOT BEING HERE.
[CHUCKLING]
OH. OH...
HERE'S THE ESTIMATE
FOR THE ROOF.
THANKS, HANK.
DON'T MENTION IT, PHYLLIS.
I HAVE AN ESTIMATE!
AND I'M SURE
IT'S TWICE AS MUCH
AS WHAT HANK
IS GOING TO CHARGE YOU.
FACE IT, JOY.
YOU NEVER LIKED
TO GET YOUR HANDS DIRTY.
WHEREAS THESE HANDS...
THEY LOVE THE DIRT.
SOME REPAIRS,
YOU CAN GET AN ESTIMATE FOR...
AND SOME REPAIRS,
YOU CAN'T PUT A PRICE ON.
PEOPLE ALWAYS SAY,
"YOU CAN'T TAKE IT WITH YOU."
BUT TRY DYING
AND THEN COMING BACK,
SEE IF YOU DON'T TRY
TO HOLD ONTO SOMETHING...
SOMETHING IMPORTANT.
"WHERE I SIT, THOU HAST
NO RIGHT TO STAND."
THAT DOESN'T
MAKE SENSE.
WHY WOULD I WANT
TO STAND WHERE YOU SIT?
SO MOSES JUST TOLD DEATH
TO GET LOST,
AND DEATH JUST WENT?
THAT'S SOME
FREEZE-DRIED BULLSHIT, DAISY.
YEAH, I CAN'T SEE DEATH
GIVING UP THAT EASILY.
I DON'T CARE
IF IT'S GANDHI.
IF I HAVE A POST-IT,
I'M TAKING HIS
BONY BROWN BUTT OUT.
SEE, DEATH DIDN'T
ACTUALLY TAKE MOSES.
GOD KISSED HIM.
GOD KISSED MOSES?
MM-HMM, WHEN IT WAS HIS TIME,
GOD KISSED HIM,
AND THAT'S HOW HE WENT.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
DID YOU GET TO THE PART
WHERE GOD HATES DEATH
AND PROMISES
HE'LL BANISH US FROM HEAVEN?
MAY I?
THERE'S NO PLACE FOR YOU
IN HERE, SWEETNESS.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THIS IS.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
I DON'T GET THIS ONE.
SAY WHAT YOU WANT
ABOUT MY BELIEFS,
BUT I'M PROFESSIONAL.
I'M PUNCTUAL
AND I GET THE JOB DONE.
THAT'S IT, RUBE.
THAT'S THE LAST
GODDAMN STRAW.
THIS IS FUCKING BULLSHIT,
THAT'S WHAT IT IS.
SHE'S JUST A KID, RUBE.
SHE CAN'T HANDLE IT.
FUCK THAT!
I CAN HANDLE THIS.
WHAT IS IT?
NO OFFENSE,
GEORGIE GIRL,
BUT HOW LONG HAVE YOU
BEEN IN THIS BUSINESS?
A FUCKING YEAR
AT THE MOST?
I MEAN, I'VE WORKED
MY FUCKING-- WORKED--
IT'S NOT A NEGOTIATION.
GEORGE HAS GOT THE LETTER.
ALL THESE FIREWORKS?
LET'S JUST ASSUME
THAT'S ALREADY HAPPENED
AND HELP
OUR YOUNG FRIEND
WITH HER SITUATION.
THANK YOU.
WHAT'S MY SITUATION?
V.I.P.R.
"VERY IMPORTANT PERSON REAP."
I.D.G.I.
"I DON'T GET IT."
OPEN IT ALREADY.
DID I WIN A PRIZE?
KEEP GOING.
K. LOWERDECK?
KYLE LOWERDECK, THE SINGER?
COME ON!
THIS HAS GOT TO BE
SOME UNHOLY
FUCKING MESS-UP,
BECAUSE THIS IS MY REAP.
I WAS BORN
TO DO THIS REAP.
I WAS PUT ON THIS EARTH,
AND IN THIS PLACE,
DER THE WAFFLE HAUS,
TO FUCKING
DO THIS REAP.
[SINGING OFF-KEY]
[SUSTAINS OFF-KEY NOTE]
PLEASE DON'T.
I WAS BORN
TO BE A ROCK STAR.
IF I COULD SING.
HE'S CUTE.
HE'S NOT AS CUTE
AS MY FIRST V.I.P.R.--
JAMES DEAN.
BEAUTIFUL  PORSCHE.
THESE REALLY DELICATE LIPS.
BUT HE WAS SO CONFUSED.
DID HE TRY TO NAIL YOU?
NO. I DON'T WHY.
I DO.
YOU.
AND YOU.
FINE.
OKAY... WHY DON'T YOU
JUST GET A BIG LEAD POLE,
AND STICK IT
RIGHT UP MY ASS?
SAME LOCATION,
DIFFERENT REAP.
YOU GOT SLOPPY SECONDS.
I'M GOING TO BE CALM.
WHY DOES SHE GET
THE COOL REAP?
PROBABLY BECAUSE
YOU'RE A FUCK-UP.
CONGRATULATIONS, GEORGIA.
YOU'VE ARRIVED.
EXCUSE ME.
I COULD'VE
BEEN JAMES DEAN,
YOU KNOW,
IF I COULD ACT...
OR DRIVE.
YOU UP FOR THIS?
YEAH, SURE, WHY NOT?
SHE'S GOING TO FUCK IT UP.
HEY, SOMEONE THINKS
I'M DOING A GOOD JOB. RIGHT?
AM I RIGHT OR AM I RIGHT?
OKAY, RICH GIRL,
BREAKFAST IS ON YOU.
ROXY!
ROXY. OH...
[PANTING]
LISTEN, UH...
GEORGE IS GOING TO NEED HELP.
SHE'LL BE FINE.
WELL, UH...
AN EVENT LIKE THAT,
PROBABLY GOING TO HAVE
POLICE SECURITY, RIGHT?
YOU CAN STOP RIGHT THERE.
I'M NOT LOSING
MY JOB OVER THIS.
IN CASE YOU HAVEN'T NOTICED,
I'M A POLICE OFFICER.
I SWORE AN OATH.
I DON'T CARE
IF YOU DONATED A KIDNEY.
WHAT YOU ARE
IS A REAPER.
THAT'S THE JOB YOU'RE
NOT GOING TO LOSE,
WHETHER YOU
WANT TO OR NOT.
WHAT IF I SAY NO?
SAY NO.
NO.
ALL RIGHT, REGGIE GETS
OUT OF SCHOOL AT 2:30,
SO IF YOU'RE REALLY
GOING TO DO THIS,
I NEED TO HAVE--
OH, GOD.
YOU KNOW, MOM,
YOU CAN'T TAKE CARE OF REGGIE
AND CHANNEL HIAWATHA
AT THE SAME TIME.
REGGIE ISN'T READY
FOR YOUR... VERSION
OF THE HEALING PROCESS.
REGGIE IS OLD ENOUGH
TO MAKE HER OWN DECISIONS.
NO, MOTHER,
SHE'S NOT.
ALL RIGHT?
SHE'S 11.
"THE PATH OF CARE IS THE ONE
WE CARVE FOR OURSELVES."
YOU'VE BEEN SAYING THAT FOR
AS LONG AS I'VE WORN A BRA,
AND I STILL HAVE NO CLUE
WHAT IT MEANS.
JUST, PLEASE,
LEAVE REGGIE OUT OF...
YOUR HOCUS POCUS.
RULES ARE THE FIRST STEP
TOWARD TYRANNY OF THE SOUL.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THE RULES ARE JUST
GETTING IN THE WAY.
AH, THAT'S GOOD.
REGGIE, YOU KNOW
ALL THAT STUFF
ABOUT GOING TO SCHOOL
AND BRUSHING YOUR TEETH,
NOT TALKING TO STRANGERS?
JUST FORGET
ABOUT ALL THAT, OKAY?
YOU CAN JUST DO
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
DO YOU NEED SOME MONEY
FOR DRUGS?
WHY ARE YOU
SUCH A FREAK?
ASK YOUR GRANDMOTHER.
WHERE'S SHE GOING?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOUR MOTHER WAS NEVER
VERY GOOD ABOUT SHARING.
YOU HAVE TO
TAKE ME TO SCHOOL.
OH, YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO SCHOOL TODAY.
WHAT AM I DOING?
CAN YOU KEEP A SECRET?
I HAD A SECRET...
I HAD A DATE
WITH A ROCK STAR...
AND NOBODY KNEW.
[LOWERDECK]
♪ WELL, WELL
♪ SO I CAN DIE EASY
♪ JESUS GONNA MAKE UP
SWEET JESUS GONNA MAKE UP ♪
♪ MY DYING BED
HOLY SMOKE!
WHAT THE FUCK?
SORRY!
♪ LORD, IN MY TIME
OF DYING ♪
♪ DON'T WANT NOBODY
TO CRY... ♪
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
IT'S LOWERDECK,
FROM "LOWERDECK"--
"IN ALL HIS GLORY."
OH, YOU'RE A FAN?
OH, I'M A FAN.
I'M A BIG FAN.
OH, MISTY, PLEASE DON'T.
DO YOU HAVE ANY?
I, UH... NO.
MILLIE, UM, I WAS
WONDERING IF YOU COULD--
EXCUSE ME.
ARE YOU WATCHING
TONIGHT?
IT'S GOING TO BE
TOTALLY LIVE.
I KNOW.
I'M... GOING.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
IT'S LIKE ONE OF THOSE
UNPLUGGED SESSIONS.
NO ONE GETS IN.
WELL, I GUESS I'M LUCKY.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE
NEAR HIM,
AND NOW I'M NEAR YOU.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL,
REALLY. I--
OH!
I, UH, UM--
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
I'M NOT A LESBIAN.
MILLIE,
WE'VE ALL EXPERIMENTED.
YOU--I HAVEN'T.
IT'S NOT AS IF
I DIDN'T GO TO COLLEGE.
WE'VE ALL PUT OUR BIG TOE
IN THAT WATER.
I REALLY HAVEN'T.
DELORES?
[HITS KEY]
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU'RE YOUNG
LIKE YOU ARE, MILLIE,
IT'S EASY.
MAN, WOMAN, BOTTOM, TOP...
SEX IS THIS BIG BUFFET,
AND YOU'RE JUST A FAT MAN
WITH A FORK,
BUT AS YOU GET OLDER,
IT'S HARDER TO GET A FORK.
OKAY. THANKS.
UM, I HAVE TO
LEAVE EARLY TODAY.
ANOTHER DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT?NO.
A.A. MEETING?NO.
WHAT, THEN?A ROCK CONCERT.
ENJOY THE BUFFET, MILLIE.
YEAH. OKAY, THANKS. BYE.
[SIGHS]
I'D LIKE TO GET A TICKET FOR
THE KYLE LOWERDECK CONCERT.
[TICKET CLERK]
SOLD OUT.
I HAVE $500?
OH, WELL,
IN THAT CASE...
SOLD OUT.
ASSHOLE.
AHEM. THAT SENSATION
YOU'RE FEELING...
WOULDN'T BE THE SENSATION
OF UTTER FAILURE, WOULD IT?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I'VE COME
TO SAVE YOUR ASS.
LET'S GO TO THE CONCERT.
YOU SCORED TICKETS?
NO.
THEN I'M SCREWED!
SERIOUSLY, I'M ROYALLY FUCKED.
ROXY'S DOWNSTAIRS.
POLICE ESCORT.
COOL.
THOSE ARE MOM'S.
I KNOW.
DO YOU EVER LOOK AT THESE
WHEN SHE'S NOT HOME?
IT'S ALL RIGHT TO BE
CURIOUS, REGGIE.
DEATH IS THE BIGGEST
MYSTERY IN LIFE.
I'D BE WORRIED ABOUT YOU
IF YOU WEREN'T CURIOUS.
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN
TO THAT PLACE, REGGIE?
THAT PLACE
WHERE GEORGE DIED?MM-MM.
IT'S AN IMPORTANT PLACE
IN HER LIFE.
IT SHOULD BE
AN IMPORTANT PLACE
IN YOURS, TOO.
I KNOW.
WE HAVE TO FIND
THE THINGS AND THE PLACES
THAT KEEP GEORGE ALIVE.
THEY'RE EVERYWHERE.
HER--HER SPIRIT...
IT'S ALL AROUND US.
SOMETIMES... I HEAR THINGS.
ME, TOO.
ARE THESE
ALL OF YOUR COOL TOPS?
SOME OF THEM ARE DIRTY.
YOU WANT TO SEE THOSE?
I LOVED RIDING
IN THE FRONT SEAT
OF THAT POLICE CRUISER.
IT WAS MY FIRST TIME
WITHOUT HANDCUFFS.
IT'S A DAY
OF FIRSTS.
UGH!
THIS IS CUTE.
IS THIS BLOOD?
NO. BRAIN.
LAST TUESDAY,
THAT GUY WHO TOOK THE
SHOTGUN TO THE FACE.
DAISY SWORE
SHE COULD GET IT OUT.
PROMISES, PROMISES.
I ALSO LOVED THE FACT
YOU WERE IN THE BACK SEAT,
GEORGE.
YOU LOOKED JUST LIKE A PERP.
YOU ARE JUST
SO PISSED OFF
THAT I GOT A ROCK STAR
AND YOU DIDN'T.
YOU JUST WISH
YOU WERE ME, DON'T YOU?
SHE'S A COCKY
LITTLE THING, ISN'T SHE?
I'M NOT COCKY.
I'M JUST COOLER
THAN YOU ARE.
[MIMICKING MASON]
I GOT A ROCK'N'ROLL REAP.
UP YOURS.
THERE'S NOTHING
TO WEAR TO IT.
MY ONLY V.I.P. REAP
WAS CHARLTON HESTON.
HE ISN'T DEAD.
YEAH, BUT ISN'T HE REALLY?
DID RUBE GET A LOT
OF BIG REAPS?
I BET HE HAS.
RUBE IS SO FUCKING OLD,
HE REAPED JESUS.
COME ON, GUYS,
I DON'T SEE WHAT THESE
CLOTHES HAVE GOT TO DO
WITH GETTING TICKETS
TO THE FUCKING ROCK CONCERT.
GEORGE IS A GIRL.
LOOKING GOOD
ISHER TICKET.
YOU HAVE A POLICE BADGE
AND A BLOODY GUN!
AND GEORGE
IS YOUNG AND CUTE.
ARE THESE
ALL YOUR TOPS?
HEY, A DEAD GIRL
HAS GOT TO MAKE DO
WITH VERY LITTLE.
I NEED SOMETHING RACY
AND CLINGY.
YOU STILL
GOT THAT $500?
MOST OF IT.
OOH, ARE WE GOING
TO GO SCALPING?
SHOPPING.
AND YOU'RE
ON YOUR OWN.WHAT?
I DON'T LIKE
YOUR FUCKING ATTITUDE.
YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN.
YOU'RE JOKING!
WHAT?
NO, BUT--
WELL, I'M JUST--
DO YOU TWO THINK
I REALLY NEED YOU
TO GET INTO
A ROCK'N'ROLL ESTABLISHMENT?
NO, I DON'T.
I WAS BORN IN
A ROCK'N'ROLL ESTABLISHMENT.
I ACTUALLY WAS.
BEHIND THE AMPS, BACKSTAGE.
[CAR ENGINE STARTING]
ROXY?
[CAR DRIVES AWAY]
I'M SO VICIOUSLY FUCKED.
[RIBBIT]
[KNOCKING]
FATHER MATTHIAS?
CONFESSION IS CLOSED.
I KNOW, I JUST...
WELL, IT'S OCCUPIED ANYWAY.
A BOY AND A GIRL ARE ACTUALLY
DESECRATING
THE CONFESSIONAL.
THEY ARE FRUITFUL
AND MULTIPLYING...
ARE YOU DRUNK,
FATHER?
I'M SORRY. I'M NOT BEING
A VERY GOOD PRIEST.
NO, YOU CERTAINLY AREN'T.
I KNOW YOU.
WERE YOU HERE FOR CONFESSION
A COUPLE OF WEEKS AGO?
I WAS.
WERE YOU THE ONE
WHO STOLE A CROSS
FROM A DEAD WOMAN?
WELL, IF YOU WANT
TO PUT IT THAT WAY, FINE.
IT'S VERY BEAUTIFUL.
THANK YOU.
SO ARE YOU.
FATHER...
TSK, TSK.
WELL, I'VE DONE
THE DRINKING.
AND THE COVETING,
THAT'S A GIVEN.
BUT THAT'S WHERE I STOP.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
DAISY ADAIR.
MY PARISH IS POOR.
I'VE SPENT A LIFETIME
TRYING TO BRING HOPE
TO THE HOPELESS,
CONVINCING THEM
THAT THERE'S SOME
GREAT REWARD AHEAD.
I WORRY ABOUT
THE HEARTS OF MEN, DAISY.
SO DO I.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO KNOW
THE SECRETS OF THE UNIVERSE,
DAISY?
WE ARE BORN.
WE DIE.
WE ROT.
[LAUGHING]
IT'S ALL ONE BIG
COSMIC JOKE!
[THUD]
OH, MY LORD...
I'M WITH THE BAND,
MATE. CHEERS.
UH, EXCUSE ME, HELLO.
I'M WITH THE BAND.
WHY DON'T YOU
UNDERSTAND ME?
I'M... WITH...
THE... BAND.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
KYLE'S GOING TO SAY
WHEN HE SAYS, "WHERE'S
MY BLOODY GUITAR?"
AND I SAY, "THE FAT
BLOODY SECURITY PERSON
HELD ME UP AT THE GATE"?
ALL RIGHT.
I'M FRIENDS WITH THE DRUMMER.
WHAT'S
THE DRUMMER'S NAME?
I CALL HIM BY HIS NICKNAME,
YOU KNOW, STICKS.
HIT THE ROAD, JACK.
ROXY, THANK GOD, MAN.
FUCKING--YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'VE BEEN THROUGH HERE.
I MEAN, IN THE GOOD OLD DAYS,
YOU USED TO BE ABLE TO JUST--
SIR, STEP ASIDE.
WHAT?
SIR, DON'T LET ME
HAVE TO ASK YOU AGAIN.
STEP ASIDE.
DON'T PULL THIS
ON ME, ROXY.
DON'T--NO, DON'T GET
YOUR LITTLE FRIEND
TO COME OVER AND
ARREST ME OR ANYTHING,
BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO--ROXY!
YOU HAVE NOT HEARD
THE LAST OF THIS!
DON'T I KNOW IT.
SHE'S WITH THE BAND.
LOOK, SHE'S PRETENDING
NOT TO KNOW ME!
YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN,
KID.
DON'T FUCK THIS UP.
ROXY, YOU'RE A BUGGER.
YOU KNOW THAT DREAM WHERE
YOU'RE SITTING IN CLASS,
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN
YOU REALIZE YOU'RE NAKED?
WELL, I NEVER HAD THAT DREAM.
[GROUPIES LAUGHING]
UNTIL NOW.
HEY, DON, GET SOMEONE TO CLEAR
THE FUCKING STEP, HEY?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
SOMEONE'S GOING TO DIE
AROUND HERE.
I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
HEY, I'M JEANNIE,
AND I'M GOING
TO GET YOU A DRINK.
I'M GEORGE,
AND I'M NOT
GOING TO ARGUE.
[CHUCKLES]
SO I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
AROUND HERE BEFORE.
I'M WITH THE NETWORK.
OH. COOL.
WHAT DO YOU DO?
OKAY, YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE HERE,
BUT HAVE NO RESPONSIBILITIES.
I'M AN... INTERN.
NICE.
SO HAVE YOU MET KYLE?
NOT YET.
WELL, TWO YEARS AGO,
KYLE'S BIGGEST GIG
WAS HIS STEP-DAD'S GARAGE.
HE WAS WAITING TABLES
AT THE DAILY GRILL,
AND THIS FUCKING AGENT
FINDS HIM.
SHE'S A VAMPIRE.
REALLY HAS FANGS.
ANYWAY, JUST LIKE THAT,
NO ONE CAN GET NEAR HIM.
NO ONE CAN TOUCH HIM.
I NEED TO TOUCH HIM.
YEAH, WELL,
HIS NEW GIRLFRIEND
WILL KILL YOU FIRST.
I'M GOING TO
TOUCH HIM TONIGHT.
YEAH, WELL, GEORGE,
LIVE HARD, DIE YOUNG,
LEAVE A FUCKING
BEAUTIFUL CORPSE.
AMEN TO THAT, SISTER.
"AMEN TO THAT, SISTER?"
ONE MORE.
JUST LIKE THAT,
I WAS A ROCKER CHICK.
CHEERS.
EXCUSE ME.
YOO-HOO.
THE THING IS,
I'VE GOT THIS LITTLE
PACKAGE FOR KYLE,
YOU KNOW, IT'S A
PERFORMANCE ENHANCER.
IF YOU'RE LUCKY,
YOU CAN GET A BIT
ON THE SIDE--
[GRUNTING]
I'VE BEEN CLEAN 15 YEARS,
LOWLIFE.
FUCK YOU.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE HEARING
FROM MY BLOODY LAWYER.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I MEAN, THAT'S GOING
TO COST YOU, BIG TIME.
IF YOU GIVE ME
50 BUCKS NOW,
WE'LL FORGET ABOUT
THE WHOLE THING.
HOW MUCH TO BREAK
BOTH YOUR LEGS?
[WHIMPERS]
OH, COME ON!
THIS ISN'T ROCK'N'ROLL.
WHAT DO YOU
SMELL LIKE?
UH...
[SNIFFS]
OH, COME ON,
SINCE WHEN DOES A MAN
NEED TO SHOWER
TO BE ROCK AND ROLL, EH?
YOU SMELL LIKE DEATH.
YOU ARE NOT EXACTLY
A BOUQUET
OF FUCKING ROSES
EITHER, LOVE, ALL RIGHT?
[FANS CHEERING]
OH, FUCK OFF.
HAVE A GOOD EVENING, SIR.
HUH?
SWEET!
OH, MAMA, I'M HOME.
COME ON.
BANDAR WANTS
TO MEET YOU.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
MASON.
WHEN KYLE USED TO PLAY,
IT WAS LIKE...
A HAPPENING, YOU KNOW?
NONE OF THIS
MANUFACTURED CRAP.
WHEREVER HE PLAYED,
PEOPLE WOULD JUST
HEAR ABOUT IT AND COME,
YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M SAYING?
SURE.
WELL, IT'S NOT
LIKE THAT ANYMORE.
IT USED TO BE
ALL ABOUT ROCK.
NOW IT'S ALL ABOUT
THE ROCK STAR.
YEAH, UM, CAN YOU
INTRODUCE ME NOW?
MM, I THINK THERE'RE
A FEW OTHER PEOPLE
WHO WANT
TO MEET YOU FIRST.
WHAT'S THEIR DEAL?
I BELIEVE THE DEAL
IS THAT YOU'RE HOT.
I AM?
YEAH.
YOU'RE ACTUALLY
KYLE'S TYPE.
YOU KNOW, THAT
EFFORTLESS COOL LOOK.
ALTHOUGH, YOU COULD USE
A LITTLE LIP GLOSS.
DO ME.
YEAH, YOU WISH, DUDE.
WHAT THE HELL
DO THEY THINK?
LET'S GO CHECK OUT
THE BUFFET.
OKAY.
I DIED IN 1938.
WHICH INTERRUPTED
A VERY PROMISING CAREER
ON THE SILVER SCREEN.
SO NOW I STAY HERE,
AND I HELP OTHER PEOPLE GO.
AND THEY DO GO
SOMEWHERE,
I KNOW THAT MUCH.
I DON'T KNOW
IF THERE'S A HEAVEN OR A HELL,
BUT I BELIEVE THERE'S MORE.
MY WHOLE LIFE...
MY WHOLE DEATH,
SHOWS ME THAT THERE'S MORE.
I JUST DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
THANK YOU.
YOU CAN'T TELL ANYONE.
I...
[SNIFFS]
I HAVE TO,
I HAVE TO TELL THEM.
YEAH.
I KNOW YOU DO.
THANK YOU FOR GIVING ME BACK
MY FAITH.
SO...
IS IT TRUE?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE HELL
SHE'S TALKING ABOUT, BAND-AID,
BUT I DO WANT
A BIT MORE TEQUILA.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
IT'S BANDAR,
MOTHERFUCKER.
LOOK INTO HIS EYES.
HE'S DEAD.
YOU'RE DEAD, RIGHT?
NO, MAN, I'M DEATHLY
ATTRACTED TO YOU.
I'M DEAD ON ARRIVAL
AT YOUR DOORSTEP.
I'M DEAD SERIOUS.
DON'T YOU GET IT?
YOU'RE WITH FRIENDS NOW.
JUST ANSWER THE QUESTION.
ARE YOU DEAD?
I WAS DEAD.
AND NOW I'M NOT.
I'M A GRIM REAPER.
I TAKE PEOPLE'S SOULS
BEFORE THEY DIE.
I KNEW IT.
WHAT IS IT LIKE
TO TAKE SOMEONE'S SOUL?
ALL RIGHT, BANDAR,
YOU KNOW WHEN
YOU'RE PISS DRUNK,
AND YOU COLLAPSE
ON THE FLOOR,
AND SOMEONE COMES
TO WAKE YOU UP
BECAUSE THE POLICE ARE
JUST ABOUT TO ARRIVE, YEAH?
WELL, I'M THAT SOMEONE.
AND AT FIRST,
THEY DON'T KNOW
WHERE THEY ARE
OR WHO THEY ARE,
AND THEY'RE
A LITTLE BIT CONFUSED.
WELL, THAT'S WHY
I'M THERE,
'CAUSE I'M THERE TO...
I'M THERE
TO REASSURE THEM.
TO MAKE THEM BELIEVE
EVERYTHING'S ALL RIGHT.
TO DEATH.
AH... NICE.
TONIGHT.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU!
THANK YOU. THANK YOU.
THANK YOU! THANK YOU!
THANK YOU!
[GIGGLING]
WHO'S THERE?
TOMMY RYAN,
IF THAT'S YOU MAKING OUT
WITH CINDY STEVENS AGAIN
IN MY CONFESSIONAL,
THERE'LL BE HELL TO PAY!
[GIRL] CINDY STEVENS?
YOU ASSHOLE!
AFTERNOON.
UH, WE WERE--
WE WERE JUST--
DON'T LIE, TOMMY.
NOT ON THIS DAY.
THIS IS A HOLY DAY,
FOR I HAVE SEEN
SOMETHING WONDERFUL.
NOW, FALL TO YOUR KNEES
AND ASK FOR HIS FORGIVENESS.
JESUS, FATHER!
DO NOT USE HIS NAME IN VAIN!
FOR HE IS REAL!
CHILL, FATHER.
YOU'RE FREAKING ME OUT.
WAIT!
LISTEN TO ME,
I HAVE SEEN
SOMETHING WONDERFUL!
TOMMY! NO, WAIT!
WAIT! TOMMY!
NO, WAIT! WAIT!
WAIT, I--
[GURGLING]
SO...
IS THAT
ALL THERE IS?
NO.
THIS IS ONLY THE START.
LOOK.
FATHER?YES?
IS IT ALL THEY SAY IT IS?
I'M AS CURIOUS
AS YOU ARE, DAISY.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
I KNOW THERE'S
A MUCH BETTER PLACE OUT THERE.
IF I COULD ONLY FIGURE OUT
HOW TO ACCESS IT.
THE BETTER PLACE OUT THERE,
IN MY MIND?
IT'S THE V.I.P. ROOM.
AND TONIGHT...
I'M FINALLY GETTING IN.
READY TO MEET KYLE?
READY FOR YOUR BRUSH
WITH IMMORTALITY?
YEAH, A BRUSH
SOUNDS RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
HEY, JEANNIE.HEY, KYLE.
I SAW YOUR MOM.
SHE SAYS HI.
OH. THANKS.
UM, THIS IS GEORGE.
SHE'S WITH THE NETWORK.
ACTUALLY,
I'M AN INTERN.
UH, JENNY...
IT'S JEANNIE.
YEAH.
KYLE DOESN'T DO
MEET-AND-GREETS
THIS CLOSE TO PERFORMANCE.
PLEASE TRY
TO RESPECT THAT.
OH...KAY.
SHE JUST TOTALLY
ROCK-BLOCKED US.
THAT WASN'T COOL.
WELL, LET'S BLOW.
I'M GOING TO
STICK AROUND AWHILE.
HE'S NOT REALLY
IMMORTAL, YOU KNOW.
YOU CAN TOUCH HIM,
BUT NOTHING'S GOING
TO BRUSH OFF ON YOU.
IT'S ONE THING TO SHOW UP,
TAKE A SOUL,
GET ON WITH YOUR AFTERLIFE.
YOU CAN THINK OF YOURSELF
LIKE SOME KIND OF...
ACCIDENT.
BUT WHEN YOU HAVE TO
WORK AT IT,
IT FEELS MORE LIKE... MURDER.
OFFER YOU A LIFT HOME?
WHY, RUBE,
IS THERE A GENTLEMAN
LURKING UNDERNEATH
THAT COLD DEMEANOR?
WHERE'S YOUR CROSS?
HE'S A PRIEST,
FOR GOD'S SAKE.
I WANTED GOLDEN TRUMPETS
AND ANGELS SINGING.
I JUST EXPECTED IT
TO BE FAR MORE GLAMOROUS.
THERE'S A PLACE
IN BOMBAY.
IT'S CALLED
THE TOWER OF SILENCE.
WHEN SOMEBODY DIES,
THEY HAVE NO MORE USE
FOR THIS BODY,
FOR THIS VESSEL,
SO THEY PUT THE BODY
AT THE TOP OF THE TOWER
AND LET THE VULTURES
HAVE AT IT.
OUR ENDINGS,
DAISY...
THEY ARE WHAT THEY ARE.
GREAT.
SO?
FIND WHAT
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR?
I KNEW
WE'D FIND YOU HERE.
WHAT--WHAT
ARE YOU DOING?
I'M BRINGING REGGIE
TO VISIT HER SISTER.
REGGIE, DID YOU EVEN
GO TO SCHOOL TODAY?
THE TRUTH, REGGIE.
MOM.
WE DID YOGA.
OH. GOOD GOD.
MOTHER, WHAT COLOR IS THE SKY
ON YOUR PLANET?
IT'S A VERY BRIGHT BLUE.
OH, I CAN'T...
I CAN'T DO THIS RIGHT NOW.
REGGIE, LET'S GO.
I'VE NEVER
BEEN HERE BEFORE.
I WANT TO STAY.
REGGIE...
SHE'S NEVER BEEN HERE
BEFORE, JOY.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
LET'S BE HERE.
HOW DO I BECOME
A REAPER?
HOW DO YOU...
BANDAR, FIRST OF ALL,
YOU HAVE TO EXPERIENCE
THE INCONVENIENCE OF DYING.
[SNORTS]
I CAN DO THAT.
DON'T YOU THINK THIS IS A BIT
BLOODY MORBID, THOUGH?
IT'S LIKE,
I CAN PROMISE YOU,
DEATH WILL FIND YOU.
YOU DON'T
HAVE TO INVITE IT IN.
YOU'RE NEVER MORE ALIVE
UNTIL YOU'RE CLOSEST TO DEATH.
VERY, VERY RIGHT.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
GET OFF. OH...
[KYLE]
♪ WELL, MEET ME, JESUS
♪ MEET ME
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE AIR ♪
♪ IF THESE WINGS
SHOULD FAIL ME ♪
♪ LORD, WON'T YOU MEET ME
WITH ANOTHER PAIR? ♪
THAT'S ALL YOU GUYS GET
RIGHT NOW.
[APPLAUSE]
WELL, LET'S HAVE
A GREAT NIGHT, GUYS.
MAYBE THIS IS OUR TIME.
MAYBE THIS IS OUR MOMENT.
LET'S ENJOY. CHEERS.
ALL RIGHT!
IT'S ALWAYS THE SAME,
WHETHER
IT'S ASKING SOMEONE OUT,
JUMPING IN THE WATER,
OR LOSING YOUR VIRGINITY.
THEY ALWAYS
SAY THE SAME THING--
JUST DO IT.
MY VERY IMPORTANT PROBLEM WAS,
I'D NEVER DONE ANY OF THOSE
VERY IMPORTANT THINGS.
HI. I'M GEORGE.
HI. I'M KYLE.
I WAS JUST, YOU KNOW,
TAKING A MOMENT...
MM.
TAKE AS MANY AS YOU CAN.
YOU EXCITED ABOUT TONIGHT?
MOSTLY NERVOUS.
ME TOO.
I MEAN, I DON'T WANT
TO DISAPPOINT THEM.
UH...
I'VE NEVER DONE
A LIVE CONCERT
ON T.V. BEFORE.
THERE'S GOING TO BE
A LOT OF PEOPLE
WATCHING TONIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW WHY,
BUT FOR SOME REASON,
I'VE BEEN PICKED
TO DO THIS.
IT'S CRAZY.
IT'S WAY TOO MUCH
RESPONSIBILITY, YOU KNOW?
YOU'RE GOING TO BE GREAT.
GIVE ME LUCK.
YOU KNOW WHAT, GUYS,
IT HAS BEEN SUCH A TREAT,
BUT I'VE GOT THINGS TO DO.
OKAY, I'LL SEE YOU
AROUND, ALL RIGHT?
WAIT. NO.WHAT IS THAT?
YOU HAVE TO GIVE THAT
BACK TO ME, ALL RIGHT?
I'M GOING TO DIE TONIGHT.
AND YOU ARE GOING
TO TAKE MY SOUL.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
I AM BANDAR.
YOUR REAL NAME,
STUPID ASSHOLE.
IT'S FRED.
IT'S FRED SWIRSKY.
I'M FUCKING
WITH YOU GUYS, MAN.
I'M NOT A FUCKING
GRIM REAPER.
JESUS CHRIST.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE THIS
DEATH WISH COMES IN,
BUT IT'S STUPID.
I DON'T THINK YOU KNOW
HOW STUPID IT IS.
YOU NEED TO GET
A LIFE, FRED.
YOU ALL NEED TO GET
SOME COLOR.
MAYBE A LITTLE ROUGE
AROUND THE CHEEKS.
SOME SUNSHINE, ALL RIGHT?
YOU, STAY CHALKY.
YOU'RE GORGEOUS.
SEE YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
YOU GUYS.
THANKS FOR COMING OUT
THIS EVENING.
♪ NOW, IN MY TIME OF DYING
♪ I DON'T WANT
NOBODY TO MOURN ♪
♪ ALL I WANT
MY FRIENDS TO DO ♪
♪ COMIN' FOR MY DYING ARMS
♪ WELL, WELL, WELL
♪ SO I CAN DIE EASY
♪ SO I CAN DIE YOUNG
♪ WELL, WELL, WELL
[GROWLING]
♪ SO I CAN DIE EASY
♪ JESUS GONNA MAKE UP
JESUS GONNA MAKE UP ♪
MY DYING BED-- ♪
[FANS SCREAMING]
NO, DON'T. PLEASE.
WOW.
WHAT'S THIS GIRL'S NAME?
WHAT IS HER NAME?
UH, JEANNIE BEAD.
FUCK!
DON'T... DON'T TOUCH ME.
[SIREN WAILS]
WHAT'S THIS?
IT'S FOR YOU.
WOW.
DOES EVERYONE
GET THIS?
NO.
DID YOU GET THIS?
NO, NO LIGHTS FOR ME.
NOT YET.
EVERY DAY,
I WATCH PEOPLE DIE.
WHY ONE DEATH MEANS MORE
THAN ANOTHER,
I HAVE NO IDEA.
I THINK PEOPLE NEED
SOMETHING FAMILIAR.
REGGIE?
MOM?
SOMETHING THEY CAN REMEMBER.
WHATCHA DOING
THERE, REGGIE?
GRANDMA'S HELPING GEORGE
WITH HER BARDO.
IS THAT RIGHT?
THE BARDO IS THE WAY
THE TIBETANS HELP THE DEAD
SORT OUT REALITY.
IT'S AN ANCIENT AND
RESPECTED RITUAL, JOY.
WELL, I BROUGHT ANOTHER
ANCIENT AND RESPECTED RITUAL.
CHUNKY MONKEY.
REGGIE,
WHY DON'T YOU GO
SCOOP US UP
A FEW BOWLS?
[SINGING]
[SIGHS]
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE
NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHO'S LOST GEORGE.
THE WHOLE WORLD
HAS LOST A SOUL.
SHE WAS MY DAUGHTER.
MINE.
SHE WAS ME, MOM.
THE SAME WAY
THAT YOU'RE ME.
AND I MISS YOU.
BOTH OF YOU.
YOU SEE IT OUT THERE?
GEORGE DID GOOD.
MM-HMM.
SHE DID FINE.
WHAT'S GOING ON, ROX?
I HAD TO SHOOT SOMEONE.
SOMEONE DIED.
DID YOUR JOB.
MINE AND MASON'S.
I MEANT YOUR OTHER JOB...
OFFICER.
I'M JUST STATING A FACT.
DID SOMEBODY
IMPORTANT DIE?
TODAY, EVERY DAY.
WHAT KIND OF PIE
YOU GOT TONIGHT?
IT'S PECAN.
I SAVED YOU A PIECE,
FOR MY VERY
IMPORTANT CUSTOMER.
GEORGE?
YEAH, SHE DID
REALLY WELL.
I CAN'T GO IN THERE
TONIGHT
AND FACE THE BOSS MAN.
DO ME A FAVOR AND...
TELL HIM I'M PISS DRUNK
SOMEWHERE IN THE GUTTER.
DON'T MAKE MORE OF IT
THAN IT IS.
I WON'T.
COME ON INSIDE.
I'M BUYING.
MAYBE IT'S EASIER TO MOURN
SOMEONE YOU NEVER REALLY KNEW.
I'M NOT SURE I GET IT,
ALL THIS SHARED PAIN...
I GUESS IT'S A PLACE
TO LEAVE A SIGN,
A WAY OF SAYING
THAT YOU LOST SOMEONE, TOO.
EVERYONE WAS CONNECTING.
EVERYONE, OF COURSE,
EXCEPT ME.
OKAY, RUBE, I BLEW IT.
I COMPLETELY BLEW IT,
AND BELIEVE ME, I'M
SO PAINFULLY, PAINFULLY AWARE
OF MY FAILURES
THIS EVENING,
BUT, SAYING THAT,
BRING ON MORE PAIN,
BECAUSE, NO DOUBT,
I DESERVE IT, OKAY?
PECAN.
NOT BAD, EITHER.
THINK OF IT AS
A GET-OUT-OF-JAIL-FREE CARD.
NICE SHOT, ROXY.
THANKS.
HERE SHE IS.
[RUBE] LOOK AT YOU!
NICE GOING.
OW.
YEAH, IT WAS CRAZY
IN THERE.
I LIKE
YOUR OUTFIT.
THANK YOU, DAISY.
ROXY PICKED IT OUT.
HMM?
AIN'T NOTHING BUT WOMAN
UNDER THIS UNIFORM.
[DAISY CHUCKLING]
WHAT THE FUCK
YOU LAUGHING AT?
NOT EVERY DEATH
GETS A CANDLELIGHT VIGIL.
MOST DEATHS,
THEY JUST GOT
A SKY FULL OF STARS.
THAT'S NOT BAD...
FOR A NOBODY LIKE ME.