[♪♪]
[GEORGE]  WHEN I WAS A KID,
MY PARENTS WOULD TELL ME
TO HOLD ON TO THINGS TIGHTLY--
A KITE, A BALLOON, WHATEVER--
TO NOT LET GO...
BUT I WAS SCARED
THAT IF I HELD ON TOO TIGHTLY
TO SOMETHING
OR TO SOMEONE,
I'D BE CARRIED AWAY.
EXCEPT I'M THE ONE
ALWAYS TELLING PEOPLE
IT'S OVER,
TIME TO MOVE ON.
THAT'S WHAT GRIM REAPERS DO.
[MAN CLEARS THROAT]
AND NOW I'M CROUCHING
IN THE BUSHES
OUTSIDE A BULLSHIT
COUNTRY CLUB,
HOPING TO GET A LOOK AT
THE BOY I CAN'T LET GO OF.
WHAT THE FUCK?
HE DISAPPEARED.
HE DIDN'T CALL.
IT WAS MY FIRST TIME.
WHAT AN ASSHOLE.
REALLY, ALL I WANTED TO DO
WAS TELL SOMEBODY
WHAT HAD HAPPENED,
TELL THEM WHAT I HAD BECOME.
I'M A STALKER.
I HAD A STALKER ONCE.
YEAH, HE WAS
A SWEET BOY.
HE'D LEAVE ME
WILDFLOWERS--
DEAD WILDFLOWERS--
AND LITTLE SPARROWS.
DOESN'T ANYONE WANT
TO KNOW WHY I'M A STALKER?
HOW'D YOU
GET RID OF HIM?
I STABBED HIM
WITH GARDEN SHEARS.
DID YOU KILL HIM?
NO, I STABBED HIM
RIGHT HERE.
WHOO. I WOULD HAVE
STALKED YOU, DAISY.
I WOULD HAVE STALKED YOU.
WHAT IS IT THAT
YOU'RE DOING NOW?
PLEASE, COME ON.
I'M NOT STALKING YOU.
I'M PERSISTENT.
WELL, I'M STALKING
SOMEONE NOW.
WHO WANTS TO GUESS WHY?
WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE,
SWEETIE?
REVENGE.
WE'RE OUT OF THAT.
ANYTHING ELSE LOOK GOOD?
OATMEAL WITH RAISINS.
WHY ARE YOU
STALKING SOMEBODY?
WHY WOULD YOU BE
STALKING ANYONE AT ALL?
OH, SHIT,
IT'S JOHNNY LAW.
I'M NOT EXACTLY
STALKING ANYONE.
I'M...YOU'RE WHAT?
I'M JUST...SPIT IT OUT.
I'M HAVING OATMEAL.
WITH RAISINS.
WELL. I'M GLAD
WE GOT THAT SETTLED.
HOW DID THAT THING
WITH THAT TRIP BLOKE
WORK OUT, GEORGE?
WE SLEPT TOGETHER,
AND THEN HE BLEW ME OFF.
NOT MY TYPE.
YEAH, HE'S ALIVE.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
IS THAT RUBE'S DATEBOOK?
WHY HAVE YOU GOT HIS BOOKS?
ARE YOU CARRYING
THEM NOW, ROXY?
CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
DOES HE LET YOU
CLEAN HIS ERASERS?
RUBE ISN'T HERE.
AND YOU'RE
SUBSTITUTE TEACHER?
HE CAN'T JUST LEAVE
AND NOT TELL ME.
FUCKING MEN.
CALM DOWN.
HE'LL BE BACK.
I DON'T THINK YOU
SHOULD GET TO BE RUBE.
I THINK I SHOULD
GET TO BE RUBE.
MASON, I WILL SHOOT YOU
WHERE YOU BETTER PRAY
IT GROWS BACK.
THERE YOU GO, ROXY.
HERE ARE YOUR
REAP REPORTS.
JUST A BRIEF DESCRIPTION
OF WHAT HAPPENED,
HOW THE PERSON DIED,
AND HOW THE REAP WENT DOWN.
FILL IT OUT.
TURN IT BACK IN.
YEAH, I DON'T DO PAPERWORK.
YOU CAN'T WRITE?
I CAN WRITE FINE.
OH, WELL, YOU'RE AN ACTRESS,
SO I DIDN'T WANT TO ASSUME.
SERIOUSLY,
WHERE IS RUBE?
PERSONAL BUSINESS, PEANUT.
DON'T CALL ME THAT.
HE CAN'T JUST NOT CALL
AND DISAPPEAR.
HERE'S YOUR OATMEAL.
I DON'T NEED OATMEAL...
OR RAISINS,
OR ANYBODY.
YOU TWO GOT ANYTHING
YOU WANT TO SAY?
ME.
I DIDN'T GET A  POST-IT.
THAT'S BECAUSE YOU'RE
GOING TO HELP GEORGE.
YOU TWO DO THE REAP,
YOU FILL OUT THE FORM,
AND THEN YOU COME BACK TO ME
FOR DEBRIEFING.
YOU GOT SOMETHING
YOU WANT TO SAY, BLONDIE?
NO, BUT THOSE DRESS BLUES
DO WONDERFUL THINGS
FOR YOUR EYES, ROXY.
I JUST...
LOVE A WOMAN
IN A UNIFORM.
WHAT YOU TRYING TO SAY?
I'M JUST A SUCKER
FOR AUTHORITY FIGURES.
YOU TWO GOT SECRETS?
I DON'T LIKE SECRETS.
I DON'T HAVE SECRETS.
I HAVE NO SECRETS.
OKAY.
WHERE'S RUBE?
HE HAS SECRETS.
[VIDEOGAME MUSIC PLAYING]
[RINGS BELL]
[VIDEOGAME STOPS]
HI.HI.
YOU NEED
SOME HELP?I DO.
GOT TO TAKE
A NUMBER, DUDE.
WELL, WHO GOT
THE FIRST ONE?
I DON'T KNOW.
I WASN'T HERE ON FRIDAY.
WELL, I NEED INFORMATION
ABOUT A WOMAN
WHO LIVED HERE
A WHILE BACK.
MARRIAGE LICENSES, DEEDS,
DEATH CERTIFICATES,
THAT SORT OF THING.
SORRY, MAN.
MRS. JACOBS DOES RECORDS.
I'M VEHICLE REGISTRATION.
SHE'S NOT HERE,
SO YOU GOT TO COME BACK.
WEDNESDAY IS RECORDS.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME, SON?
JOEY.
YOU KNOW WHAT PEOPLE SAY
ABOUT KIDS THESE DAYS, JOEY.
AH, THEY SAY
YOU'RE ALL A BUNCH
OF SELF-OBSESSED,
LAZY NUMBNUTS
WHO HAVE LOST THE CAPACITY
TO THINK FOR THEMSELVES.
WELL, IT'S NOT TRUE.
OH, I'LL KICK THEIR ASSES
FOR SAYING SO.
GOOD FOR YOU, JOEY.
HERE'S MY NUMBER.
NOW HOW ABOUT
RESTORING A DUDE'S FAITH
IN AMERICA'S YOUTH
AND HELPING ME OUT?
ANYTHING FOR AMERICA, DUDE.
YOU'RE A GOOD KID
AND FINE CITIZEN, JOEY.
KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
UH, JUST DON'T
TELL MRS. JACOBS,
BECAUSE SHE WILL
FUCK ME UP.
OH, THAT'S NOT A PROBLEM.
WHERE DO WE GO?
WELL, THIS IS,
LIKE, IT.
WE WENT DIGITAL LAST YEAR.
[SIGHS]
[VIDEOGAME MUSIC PLAYS]
OH, SORRY ABOUT THAT.
[MUSIC SHUTS OFF]
LISTEN, SWEETIE.
TONIGHT'S WITH YOUR DAD,
SO YOU'RE GOING TO NEED
TO PACK YOUR OVERNIGHT.
I'M PACKED.
NEATLY, OR DID YOU JUST
THROW EVERYTHING IN THERE?
NEATLY.
LANGENSTEIN'SIS DELIVERING
OVER SOME GROCERIES,
SO PLEASE,
TRY TO BE NICE.
WHY ARE WE GETTING
GROCERIES DELIVERED?
WELL, BECAUSE
IT MAKES MY LIFE EASIER.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
GAIL RECOMMENDED HIM.
EVERYONE'S USING HIM.
HELLO.
OH, MY GOD.
JOY LASS?
YES.
I'M VINCE
FROM  LANGENSTEIN'S.
GUARANTEED TO
BRING IT ON TIME,
EVERY TIME.
HEY, LITTLE LADY.
HI.
SO THAT'LL BE
73 ON THE NOSE.
OH, RIGHT. OKAY.
UM...
OH, GOD.
I FORGOT TO GO
TO THE F-ING A.T.M.
MOM.
I SAID "F"-ING.
UM, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I HAVE SOME MORE
MONEY UPSTAIRS,
SO I'LL JUST
RUN AND GET IT.
YOU LIKE  POP TARTS?
YEP.
YEAH, ME TOO.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
REGGIE.
YOU MARRIED?
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
WELL, I BET THE
BOYS AT SCHOOL HAVE
BIG CRUSHES ON YOU.
JUST ONE,
BUT HE'S A GEEK.
I REMEMBER
WHEN I WAS YOUR AGE,
I USED TO TOTALLY BE
AFRAID OF GIRLS.
NOW I'M NOT
AFRAID OF ANYTHING.
EVERYONE'S AFRAID
OF SOMETHING.
NOT ME.
MY SISTER'S DEAD.
OKAY.
YOU CAN ASK MY MOM
IF YOU DON'T BELIEVE ME.
SHE DIED LAST YEAR.
HOW DID SHE DIE?
SHE WAS MURDERED.
SERIOUSLY?
IN THE LIVING ROOM.
THEY NEVER FOUND WHO DID IT.
OKAY...
HERE WE GO.
72,
AND IT'S A MIRACLE, FIVE MORE.
THANKS.
BOY, THIS WAS SO EASY.
I GUESS WE'LL BE
SEEING YOU NEXT WEEK,
HMM, REGGIE?
ACTUALLY,
THIS IS NOT MY ROUTE.
I'M FILLING IN
FOR DAVEY.
YOU'LL LIKE HIM.
OH, OKAY.
BYE.
[♪♪]
THERE'S NEVER A COP AROUND
WHEN YOU NEED ONE.
AND BY THE SAME LOGIC,
WHEN A GIRL FINALLY
HAS ONE SECRET
TRULY WORTH SHARING,
THERE'S NEVER A SINGLE PERSON
AROUND TO LISTEN.
GOD! GET A ROOM.
YUCK.
WHAT'S UP, CRYSTAL?
NOTHING.
IT'S LIKE MATING SEASON
AROUND HERE.
ARE WE, LIKE,
THE ONLY TWO
IN THIS OFFICE
WHO ARE SINGLE?
I MEAN,
I DON'T MEAN TO ASSUME.
DO YOU HAVE A BOYFRIEND,
CRYSTAL?
OKAY. NICE TALKING TO YOU.
YOU TOO.
I COULDN'T TELL DELORES.
THAT WOULD BE
LIKE TELLING A PARENT,
AND THERE ARE SOME LINES
YOU JUST DON'T CROSS.
I HAVE TO
TELL YOU SOMETHING.
LET ME GUESS. YOU HAVE
A DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT
AND HAVE TO
LEAVE EARLY AGAIN.
NO.
MILLIE, THIS IS REALLY
GETTING TO BE A PAIN
IN THE KEISTER.
NO, WHAT I WAS
GOING TO TELL YOU--
[COUPLE LAUGHING]
DO YOU EVER
GET THE FEELING
THAT WE'RE, LIKE,
THE ONLY TWO PEOPLE HERE
THAT ARE SINGLE?
MILLIE, YOU SAY THAT
AS IF IT'S A BAD THING.
I HAVE AN ACTIVE
ONLINE PROFILE,
AND NOT A DAY GOES BY
THAT I DON'T RECEIVE AN E-MAIL
ABOUT YOU KNOW WHAT.
DON'T ASK.
WHAT?YOU KNOW.
NO, I DON'T KNOW.
MEN WANT ONE THING, MILLIE.
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
I'VE JUST RECEIVED AN E-MAIL
OF A SEXUALLY EXPLICIT NATURE.
DON'T LOOK.
REALLY?
OH, HE WANTS
TO MEET MURRAY.
THAT'S SWEET.
THAT'S NOT SWEET, MILLIE.
IT'S PROVOCATIVE.
I DON'T GET IT.
OH, COME ON.
HE WANTS TO...
[WHISPERING] PET MY CAT.
MAYBE HE JUST WANTS
TO MEET MURRAY.
MY GOODNESS, YOU ARE YOUNG.
ANYWAY, I'M MEETING
A NEW E-FRIEND THIS EVENING
AT THE REN FAIR,
AND MAYBE YOU THINK
WATCHING JOUSTING ALL NIGHT
DOESN'T MEAN ANYTHING.
I'M TELLING YOU,
MEN HAVE ONE THING
AND ONE THING ONLY
ON THE BRAIN.
JOUSTING?
THEY'RE PRIMAL CREATURES,
THESE--
THESE MEN.
THEY'RE AWFUL,
AREN'T THEY?
BUT THEY'RE CUTE,
AND THEY CAN'T COOK,
AND WE JUST CAN'T
HELP OURSELVES.
I GOT TO GO.
OH, I'M SORRY, MILLIE.
YOU WANTED TO
TELL ME SOMETHING.
WHAT WAS IT?
I HAVE
A DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT.
NO, THAT'S WHAT TIME
THE PILATES CLASS IS, CLANCY.
I'M GETTING IN SHAPE
FOR MYSELF, ALL RIGHT?
LOOK, CAN YOU
PICK HER UP EARLY OR NOT?
THANK YOU.
PILATES?
YEAH.
IT'S AN EXERCISE CLASS.
I KNOW WHAT IT IS.
LILY NOLAN DOES IT.
SHE'S 11.
YOU DON'T DO PILATES.
OKAY, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I LIED.
I HAVE A DATE.
NO WAY.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOUR MOTHER HAS A DATE.
WITH VINCE?
THE DELIVERY GUY?
OH, NO.
DOES IT BOTHER YOU
THAT I HAVE A DATE?
BECAUSE...
YOU KNOW...
THE THING IS, HONEY...
I MEAN, AS MUCH AS
I LOVE TO BE ALONE,
AND AS MUCH AS I LOVE
BEING YOUR MOM,
WELL, THERE'S
JUST A PART OF ME--
DAD'S GIRLFRIEND
DUMPED HIM.
REALLY?
DID HE TELL YOU THAT?
YEP.
DON'T TELL YOUR DAD
ABOUT MY DATE.
SO IF HE ASKS,
SHOULD I JUST LIE?
LIKE A RUG.
MOST PEOPLE KNOW
THAT DEATH'S COMING,
AND MOST PEOPLE
REFRAIN FROM SEEKING IT OUT.
SOME PEOPLE ARE DIFFERENT.
FRIENDOS, WE GATHER TODAY
SO THAT YOURS TRULY,
ICARUS JONES,
CAN DEMONSTRATE
THAT IT IS BETTER TO
TAKE THE SICK RISK
THAN TO SUFFER
THAT WASTING ILLNESS
OTHER PEOPLE CALL
"GETTING BY."
[CHEERING]
SOME PEOPLE
HAVE NO COMPREHENSION
THAT DEATH CAN BE SO CLOSE.
AND NOW I HAVE
A LITTLE MESSAGE
FOR ANY GRIM REAPERS
OUT THERE IN THE AUDIENCE.
I REALIZE IT MUST
BE SO FRUSTRATING
GOING HOME EMPTY-HANDED.
THIS IS SOME WEIRD SHIT.
TRUE WORDS, GEORGIE.
TRUE WORDS.
SERIOUSLY.
YOU CANNOT MESS AROUND
WITH DEATH,
AND IF DEATH IS HERE TODAY,
THEN I HAVE SOMETHING
REALLY PERSONAL
I WANT TO EXPRESS TO HIM.
OR HER.
LET ME SEE.
DEATH, YOU CAN
KISS MY SWEET ASS!
[CHEERING]
IS THAT--
IS THAT FOR US?
I BELIEVE IT IS.
THAT'S REALLY IMPOLITE.
LET'S DO THIS SHIT!
[CROWD CHEERING]
WAKE UP, MAN.
WE JUST WON
THE LOTTERY.
YEAH!
MY GOD.
YES. OH, YES!
THAT WAS SICK!
50-FOOT FREEFALL,
ALL VERTICAL.
OWW!
YOU'RE DEAD.
YOU REALIZE THAT,
DON'T YOU?
YEAH, IT HAD TO HAPPEN
SOONER OR LATER.
DON'T YOU CARE?
SURE. IT'S ALL
TRANSITION.
WHAT HAPPENS NEXT?
NO! YOU DON'T GET IT.
YOU'RE FUCKING DEAD,
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT DOESN'T TAKE
ANYTHING SPECIAL
TO JUMP OFF
A FUCKING BUILDING.
WHOA, EASY...
DON'T "WHOA, EASY" ME!
YOU WERE ALIVE,
AND NOW YOU'RE DEAD.
NO MORE JUMPING
OR DIVING OR KISSING
OR PARTYING
OR DATING OR WHATEVER.
WHAT THE FUCK
IS YOUR PROBLEM?
WHAT'S THIS?
IT'S NATIONAL, MAN.
WE'RE TIED IN TO THE
WHOLE NATIONAL DATABASE.
BOOM,
INSTANT INFORMATION.
I DON'T WANT NATIONAL.
I WANT HERE, THIS TOWN.
BUT THIS IS LIKE...
MORE.
I DON'T ENVY YOU, JOEY.
YOU LIVE IN A WORLD
WITH 12,000 MENUS
AND NOT A THING YOU CAN EAT.
HEY, I GET THAT.
I REALLY HOPE YOU DO.
DUDE.
I MEAN, THERE'S
ALWAYS THE BOXES
IN THE BASEMENT.
IS THAT RIGHT?
YEAH. COME ON.
HEY. SO...
WE'LL STOP BY
MANDARIN KING TONIGHT,
AND FOR BREAKFAST
I GOT THOSE TOASTER
THINGS YOU LIKE.
WE HAD KUNG PAO CHICKEN
LAST NIGHT,
SO TRY TO AVOID CHINESE.
BUT SHE LIKES CHINESE FOOD.
DON'T YOU, SWEETHEART?
IT'S FINE.
YOU LIKE CHINESE.
HEY, IS THAT THAT  SHALIMAR
I BOUGHT YOU?
NOPE, IT'S THE  CHANEL
I BOUGHT ME.
SO YOUR MOM SEEMS TO BE
IN GOOD SPIRITS.
TERRIFIC.
YEAH.
JEEZ, YOU GUYS
HAVE SO MUCH FOOD
IN THE HOUSE,
I'M JEALOUS.
WE HAD THIS GUY
DELIVER GROCERIES
THIS MORNING,
VINCE.
VINCE?
AND IT WAS EXPENSIVE,
LIKE 80 BUCKS FOR NOTHING.
YEAH, THAT'S
NOT LIKE YOUR MOTHER
TO THROW AWAY MONEY.
SO...
HOW ARE YOU, JOY?
I'M GREAT.
SO I HEAR YOU'VE
BEEN GETTING YOUR, UH...
GROCERIES DELIVERED.
YEAH, JUST THOUGHT
WE'D TRY SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
GOOD FOR YOU.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
WHATEVER MAKES YOU HAPPY,
AND IF IT'S...
VINCE THE GROCERY BOY,
GOOD FOR YOU.
HOW'S CHARLOTTE?SHE'S GOOD.
BIG PLANS FOR THE WEEKEND?
NOTHING SPECIAL.
ALREADY SETTLING
IN TO A ROUTINE,
I GUESS, HMM?
THAT'S HOW IT IS
WITH LONG-TERM RELATIONSHIPS.
YEP.
GOOD FOR YOU.
I'LL GO GET YOUR BAG,
SWEETHEART.
DID YOU TELL YOUR MOTHER
ABOUT CHARLOTTE AND ME?
NO.
YOU KNOW I DON'T
LIKE LYING, REGGIE.
OKAY. I TOLD HER.
SO WHAT'S YOUR MOM
UP TO THESE DAYS?
PILATES.
REGGIE'S GOT
A HUMAN DEVELOPMENT ASSIGNMENT
DUE MONDAY.
CLANCY.
MARVIN GAYE.
DUE MONDAY.
HELLO.
WELL, GET
SOMEBODY ELSE.
BILL, IT'S NOT
LIKE I'M-- I'M...
OF COURSE.
I UNDERSTAND.
[SIGHS]
I CAN BE THERE IN AN HOUR.
YOU'RE UNBELIEVABLE.
DEPARTMENT MEETING.
IT CAME COMPLETELY
OUT OF THE BLUE.
DON'T DO THIS, CLANCY.
I CAN PICK HER UP
IN THE MORNING.
YOUR PHONE DIDN'T RING.
IT WAS ON VIBRATE.
REGGIE,
YOUR FATHER HAS
AN UNEXPECTED CONFLICT.
SO YOU'LL BE STAYING
WITH ME TONIGHT.
SORRY, HONEY.
I WANT TO LIVE WITH GRANDMA.
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING]
LINDA, I GOT THOSE FLAMING
SAMBUCAS RACKED AND READY.
HI. I'LL BE WITH YOU
IN A SEC, HON.
I GOTTA GET THESE OUT.
LIKE BOOZE ISN'T
DANGEROUS ENOUGH
BY ITSELF.
HERE'S A THOUGHT.
LET'S LIGHT THE BOOZE
ON FIRE
AND HAND IT TO
DRUNK PEOPLE.
RECIPE FOR DISASTER?
THAT'S JUST
WHAT I WAS THINKING.
LISTEN, MY FRIENDS
ARE GETTING READY
TO GO TO A CLUB.
THEY WANT
TO GO DANCING--
I DON'T WANT
TO GO DANCING.
I WAS THINKING
YOU DON'T WANT
TO GO DANCING.
I WAS HOPING
INSTEAD--
YOU CAN'T
BUY ME A DRINK.
I CAN'T FINISH
A SENTENCE.
FINISH YOUR SENTENCE.
I WAS HOPING I COULD
BUY YOU A DRINK.
YOU'RE NOT A GOOD LISTENER.
I HEARD YOU.
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
HAVE CHANGED YOUR MIND.
NO, BUT THANK YOU.
THE PLEASURE'S ALL MINE.
WHO IS THAT?
HIS NAME IS RAY SUMMERS,
AND THAT IS THE FIRST TIME
I EVER SAW A WOMAN
SAY NO TO HIM.
GOOD FOR YOU.
GOOD FOR ME.
I'M LOOKING FOR
A MR. OR MRS. B. BRIGGS.
OH, YOU MEAN BUDDY.
SEE THOSE TWO COWBOYS?
THE GUY WHO WINS
IS BUDDY BRIGGS.
WHO'S NEXT?
BETTER BRING A SACK LUNCH
AND YOUR DADDY'S SHOES.
THIS IS A MAN'S GAME.
NOW WE'RE TALKING.
HELL, I'M IN THE MOOD
FOR SOME PAIN.
LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE GONNA
GET YOUR WISH, BUDDY.
HEY, PRETTY GIRL.
WHAT'LL YOU GIVE ME
IF I TAKE THIS GUY DOWN?
DAMN.
SHOW THEM A LITTLE COUNTRY,
NOW, YOU HEAR?
YOU'RE GOING DOWN, BOY.
[CROWD CHEERING]
YOU ALL RIGHT
THERE, BUDDY?
I FEEL A LITTLE WARM,
IS ALL.
WHAT THE...
[WOMAN SCREAMS][BUDDY SCREAMS]
THAT GUY'S ON FIRE.
SEVEN BALL, SIDE POCKET.
DANG, I BURNED UP.
SPONTANEOUS
HUMAN COMBUSTION.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT
THAT WAS A MYTH.
SO ARE YOU GOING
ON YOUR DATE?
HMM.
THANKS TO
YOUR FATHER, NO.
WHY IS THIS GUY
STILL COMING OVER?
WELL, BECAUSE IT'S--
IT'S MORE POLITE
TO SAY NO IN PERSON.
YOU JUST WANT TO SEE HIM.
REGGIE, I'M BEING POLITE.
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
YOU HAD A DATE?
[SIGHS]
20 YEARS AGO.
YOU HAVEN'T KISSED
ANYONE BUT DAD IN 20 YEARS?
YEAH.
DO YOU THINK
YOU FORGOT HOW?
[DOORBELL RINGS]
I REALLY DON'T THINK
THEY'VE CHANGED IT
ALL THAT MUCH.
HURRY, UPSTAIRS.
SCOOT, SCOOT.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD PRACTICE
ON YOUR ARM, LIKE THIS...
UPSTAIRS NOW.
HI, JOY.
MY GOD, YOU LOOK GREAT.
OH, THANK YOU, ANGELO.
SO THIS IS BEATRICE LANE.
AS ADVERTISED.
[SIGHS]
THIS IS GOING TO
SOUND TERRIBLE.
I-I REALLY--
I REALLY WANTED
TO DO THIS EVENING,
BUT I THOUGHT MY EX
WAS GOING TO TAKE REGGIE.
BUT I JUST FOUND OUT
THAT HE CAN'T.
OH, THAT'S NOT A PROBLEM.
LET'S JUST BRING HER ALONG.
YES!
REGGIE.
HI, REGGIE.
I'M ANGELO.
YOU REMEMBER ME?
YOU OWNED THE APARTMENT
WE LOOKED AT.
YEAH.
YOU HAVE ANY PLANS
FOR THIS EVENING, REGGIE?
WELL, YOU DO NOW.
COOL.
WELL, LET'S GO.
I'M CHANGING.
THIS, JOSEPH,
IS A SYSTEM.
EVERYTHING IN ITS PLACE,
LAID OUT.
YOU CAN TOUCH IT.
YOU CAN SEE IT.
SURE, BUT
NO INTERNET PORN.
SOMEONE EVER TELL YOU
THAT STUFF'LL
MAKE YOU GO BLIND?
ACCEPTABLE RISK.
HEY, HERE'S A BIRTH
CERTIFICATE FOR A ROSE SOFER.
THAT HELP?
LUCY'S DAUGHTER.
LET'S MAKE A PILE FOR
THIS ONE RIGHT HERE, HUH?
MAN, THIS SHIT IS OLD...
LIKE, 80 YEARS.
FUCKING... INDIANS STILL
ROAMING THE PLAINS.
YOU SMOKE A LOT
OF MARIJUANA, JOEY?
NOT TILL AFTER WORK.
YOU'D THINK SOMEONE
BURNING TO A CRISP
WOULD HAVE THINNED OUT
THE CROWD A LITTLE.
JUST BY ONE, I'M AFRAID.
I WASN'T
TALKING TO YOU.
BUT YOU
DESPERATELY WANT TO.
WANT TO LET ME
BUY YOU A DRINK OR NOT?
YOU DO WHAT
YOU WANT TO DO.
NOTED.
MACY? I'LL HAVE
ONE MORE. THANKS.
SO, WHAT,
PEOPLE AROUND HERE
JUST DON'T CARE
THAT A MAN DIED?
YOU'RE STILL HERE.
DEATH DOESN'T SCARE ME.
NOTED.
YOU WANT A DRINK,
SWEETHEART?
A SHOT OF TEQUILA.
WHAT KIND?
WHATEVER'S THE MOST EXPENSIVE.
HE'S BUYING.
SO, WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
THAT'S A LITTLE PERSONAL.
I-- I REALLY THINK
YOU SHOULD BACK OFF.
FUNNY BOY.
I KNOW IT'S RAY.
THEN WHY DID YOU ASK?
JUST MAKING
CONVERSATION.
I THINK WE'VE MOVED PAST
THAT LITTLE NUMBER.
I DON'T THINK WE HAVE.
OKAY.
THEN WHY DON'T WE START
WITH YOUR NAME,
AND WE'LL GO ON
FROM THERE.
THAT'S A LITTLE PERSONAL,
BUT THANKS FOR THE COCKTAIL.
I WANT HER.
WHOEVER SHE IS.
HEY, BARKEEP,
DOS CERVEZAS, POR FAVOR,
THEN  DOSMORE.
GRACIAS.
GEORGIE, SOME VAGUE
NOTION OF IMMORTALITY
NOTWITHSTANDING,
THAT IS NOT A PROPER WAY
TO DRIVE A CAR,
AND I SWEAR TO GOD,
I HOPE ONE OF THESE
BEERS IS MINE.
NO.
YOU MADE IT.
THANK GOD.
SHE IS IN SUCH
A BLOODY BAD MOOD.
YOU FINISHING THAT?
WHAT'S THAT SMELL?
IT SMELLS LIKE
BUFFALO WINGS.
YEAH, THAT'S BUDDY.
HE GOT BURNED.
GOOD. ONE LESS MAN
IN THE WORLD.
[BELCHES]
EXCUSE ME.
UGH.
HI. I'M RAY.
FUCK YOU, RAY.
NICE SPENDING TIME
WITH YOU GUYS.
RAY, THIS IS MASON--
MASON, RAY--
AND GEORGE.
CURIOUS GEORGE.
SO, DAISY,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I THOUGHT IT WAS
JUST THE THREE OF US.
DAISY?
DAISY ADAIR.
[RAY CHUCKLES]
SO, WHAT DO YOU DO, RAY?
I'M A TELEVISION PRODUCER,
GEORGE.
SO YOU'RE RICH?
COMFORTABLE.
I SUPPOSE YOU'RE CHARMING.
TOLERABLE.
AND WOMEN JUST FALL
THE FUCK ALL OVER YOU.
NOT YOU, I SUSPECT.
GEORGIA,
YOU'RE BEING IMPOLITE.
NO, NO,
IT'S OKAY.
EVERYBODY LIKES ME
EVENTUALLY.
OKAY, DAISY, I NEED
A WORD WITH YOU.
I DON'T THINK SO.
[BELCHES]
SO, WHAT'S YOUR DEAL,
ASSHOLE?
OH, I'M JUST HAPPY
TO MAKE A NEW FRIEND,
DAISY HERE.
DAISY, REALLY,
A WORD.
REALLY, NOT NOW.
RAY. IS IT RAY?
RAY. RAY, HEY.
SO HAS DAISY TOLD YOU
OF HER EXTENSIVE--
SOME MIGHT SAY
INTIMATE--
KNOWLEDGE OF
ERROL FLYNN?
OH, YEAH?
I LOVE THOSE OLD MOVIES.
EXCUSE US.
YOUR FLY'S UNDONE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I TOLD YOU.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT GEORGE.
SHE'S BEEN ACTING REALLY ODD.
YOU JUST SAW IT
BACK THERE, DIDN'T YOU?
SHE'S GOT A CRUSH ON A BOY.
SHE'LL BE FINE.
YOU DON'T
FUCKING UNDERSTAND.
EARLIER, IT WAS SHOUTING,
IT WAS MAYHEM,
IT WAS CHAOS, ALL RIGHT?
GEORGE IS A BIG GIRL,
AND EVEN
IF SHE'S NOT A BIG GIRL,
SHE'S A DEAD GIRL.
SHE'S GOING TO BE OKAY,
AND IN CASE
YOU HAVEN'T NOTICED,
I'M KIND OF IN THE
MIDDLE OF SOMETHING,
SO EXCUSE ME--
JUST FUCKING WAIT.
WHAT IS IT, MASON?
ALL RIGHT.
I'VE ALWAYS
FOUND YOUR STORIES
CHARMINGLY NAUGHTY.
THE LEGENDARY
BLOWJOBS OF YORE.
THEY WERE ALL QUITE ROMANTIC
IN THEIR FASHION, YOU KNOW?
THANK YOU.
I'VE NEVER ACTUALLY SEEN YOU
WITH ANOTHER MAN.
I'M NOT WITH HIM.
I'M SORRY.
I HAVE TO CHECK MY ROUGE.
WELL, MASON,
I GUESS IT'S TIME
FOR YOU TO GET
PRETTY WELL SHITFACED.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS JUST PULL ON IT
A LITTLE BIT, LIKE THAT,
AND IT TURNS.
GOOD. GOOD.
IF YOU WANT IT
TO TURN FASTER,
YOU JUST PUNCH OUT
INTO THE AIR.
JUST A LITTLE.
GOOD.
OH! NO!
I'M TERRIBLE
AT THIS.
JUST TAKES PRACTICE.
YOU GO LAUNCH IT.
YOU HAVING FUN?
YEAH. YEAH.
NOT EXACTLY
WHAT I'D HOPED FOR,
BUT...
WHAT DID YOU WANT?
WELL, YOU KNOW,
THAT WE'D HAVE
A LITTLE DINNER,
MAYBE A COUPLE
OF GLASSES OF WINE,
SOME AWKWARD
CONVERSATION,
AND THEN I ATTACK YOU.
OKAY, WELL,
THAT'S GOOD TO KNOW.
MM-HMM.
ALL RIGHT, REGGIE,
TOSS IT UP IN THE AIR!
NICE.
OKAY.
I'M READY.
MY TURN.READY?
SHOW ME WHAT TO DO.
ALL RIGHT, NOW.
GOOD.
HOLD ON.
DON'T LET GO, OKAY?
I CAN'T CONTROL IT.
JUST DON'T LET GO.
THAT'S THE THING
ABOUT KITES.
YOU HAVE TO HOLD ON TIGHT
SO THEY CAN FIGHT
AGAINST THE WIND...
THAT'S IT, GEORGIA.
THAT'S GOOD. HANG ON.
IT'S PULLING TOO HARD.
DON'T LET GO, GEORGE.
BECAUSE THE SECOND
YOU LET GO,
ALL THE LIFE
GOES OUT OF THEM.
SHIT.
[RAY] SO,
WHAT'S THAT ABOUT?
PROBABLY YOU.
I FIND YOUR FRIEND DAISY
PAINFULLY ATTRACTIVE.
TAKE A NUMBER.
HOW DO YOU KNOW HER?
THAT'S NONE
OF YOUR FUCKING BUSINESS.
YOU'RE AN ANGRY
LITTLE THING, AREN'T YOU?
YOU CALL ME
A "LITTLE THING" AGAIN,
AND I'LL PUT
THIS FUCKING DART
RIGHT BETWEEN
YOUR TWINKLING EYES.
ANOTHER TEQUILA?
PLEASE.
ARE YOU THE LOVE-'EM-
AND-LEAVE-'EM TYPE?
I'VE DONE THAT.
WHAT IS UP WITH THAT?
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
GEORGE?
SOME BOY
NOT NICE TO YOU?
NO, I'M GOOD.
I'LL BET YOU ARE.
MACY. TWO MORE.
OKAY, GEORGE,
FIVE REASONS
MEN ARE SCUM
AND WOMEN LET US
GET AWAY WITH IT.
ONE, WE ONLY WANT ONE THING,
NO EXCEPTIONS.
TWO, WE FALL
IN LOVE WITH YOU
BEFORE WE CAN
HAVE THAT THING,
AND THEN FALL BACK OUT
ONCE WE'VE HAD IT,
WHEREAS WOMEN,
CONVERSELY,
FALL IN LOVE AFTERWARDS.
THREE, WE WILL LIE, CHEAT,
STEAL, OR MURDER
IN ORDER TO GET THAT THING.
WHY AM I SUGAR-COATING THIS?
YOU'RE A BIG GIRL.
IN ORDER TO FUCK YOU.
FOUR, WE FREELY ADMIT
TO NUMBERS ONE THROUGH THREE,
AND WOMEN DON'T CARE,
AND THE NUMBER FIVE REASON
WHY MEN ARE SCUM
AND WOMEN LET US
GET AWAY WITH IT--
YOU CAN'T LIVE WITHOUT US.
HERE'S TO YOUR
BULLSHIT, RAY.
FUCKING MEN.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
HIS SURPRISE IS?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
OKAY, REGGIE.
TIME FOR BED.
IT'S 7:00.
EXACTLY. TIME FOR BED.
YOU'RE GOING TO
TRY AND KISS HIM.
WHAT IS THIS OBSESSION
WITH KISSING?
I'M 11.
OKAY, YOU TWO.
CLOSE YOUR EYES.
OH, I KNOW WHAT THIS IS.
OF COURSE, YOU DO.
THAT'S SO GOOD.
DID YOU DO THAT?
I DID TWO OF THEM.
THIS ONE'S FOR YOU.
IT LOOKS JUST LIKE HER.
SAD.
SAY GOOD NIGHT, REGGIE.
GOOD NIGHT.
AND THANK YOU
FOR THE KITE-FLYING.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
SHE LIKES YOU,
AND SHE DOESN'T
LIKE ANYBODY.
SHE SEEMED TO HAVE
A GOOD TIME.
ME TOO.
I'M GLAD.
DO YOU LIKE R & B?
[♪♪]
ALWAYS BEEN
A JAZZ MAN, MYSELF,
BUT I'D PROBABLY
BETTER GO.
AND THAT IS HOW
YOU PAY MY RENT.
YOU'RE GOOD,
MASON.YES.
GO AGAIN?
OF COURSE... RAY.
JUST FEELS SO GOOD
IN MY HAND, THIS MONEY.
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
BUT I LOVE TAKING IT
FROM YOU, RAY.
OH, COME ON.
YOU GOT A BET
ON THIS?
MY DAD USED TO SAY,
"NEVER BET ON ANYTHING
THAT CAN TALK.
IF IT CAN TALK,
IT CAN BE BOUGHT."
SO WHAT ABOUT DAISY?
WHAT ABOUT DAISY?
YOU'VE OBVIOUSLY
GOT FEELINGS FOR HER.
IF YOU WANT ME
TO STEP OFF,
NOW'S YOUR MOMENT.
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
ME AND DAISY ARE JUST FRIENDS.
SHE'S A LOVELY GIRL, BUT NO.
JUST FRIENDS, ALL RIGHT?
HEY.
WE'VE GOT NEXT.
[LAUGHS]
TAKE A WALK, JUNIOR.
THERE'S PLENTY OF
TABLES AVAILABLE.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
WHAT HE SAID.
WELL, I LIKE THIS TABLE,
SO IF YOU WOULDN'T MIND
FUCKING OFF...
EXCUSE ME. IS IT
THREE AGAINST TWO, IS IT?
BECAUSE I'LL HAVE YOU KNOW,
I'VE HAD MY ASS KICKED
BY BIGGER COCKSUCKERS
THAN YOU, ALL RIGHT?
WHOA, MASON.
WE DON'T WANT
ANY TROUBLE.
THESE FOLKS HAVE NEXT,
WE'LL GET OUT OF YOUR WAY.
DON'T TELL ME TO FUCK OFF.
I TELL PEOPLE
TO FUCK OFF.
NOW, FUCK OFF.
YOUR BREAK.
WHA...
DEATH ISN'T LIKE
HOLDING ON TO A KITE...
OR A BOY...
OR MOST ANYTHING ELSE,
BECAUSE SOMETIMES,
EVEN IF YOU WANT TO LET GO,
IT WON'T LET YOU.
THIS IS THE
LAST ONE, DUDE.
WHAT DO YOU
GOT THERE?
DEATH CERTIFICATE.
WHOSE?
THE MOTHER.
WELL, EVERYONE'S
GOT TO DIE, RIGHT?
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE GOING TO
LOVE THIS.
THIS ONE'S GOT
THE DAUGHTER'S NAME ON IT.
SORRY.
DUDE...
THIS GUY LOOKS
JUST LIKE YOU.
CAN I SEE IT?
HUH. SOUVENIR.
I WANT TO DO
A DUET. SOMETHING
COUNTRY/WESTERN.
FUCK THAT, DAISY.
I'M NOT GOING TO SING
SOME HILLBILLY BULLSHIT.
IF WE'RE GOING
TO GO HILLBILLY,
I WANT TO FIGHT.
GEORGIA, HE WORKS
FOR TELEVISION,
HE'S GORGEOUS,
AND HE WANTS ME,
SO UNLESS YOU REALLY
DO WANT A FIGHT,
YOU'RE SINGING WITH ME.
THIS ISN'T ON.
HELLO.
DAISY, I'M REALLY
NOT UP FOR THIS.
UH, EXCUSE ME, HI.
TESTING. THIS ISN'T ON.
I'M NOT SINGING.
RELAX, HAVE FUN. MEN LIKE
GIRLS WHO CAN HAVE FUN.
IS THAT WHAT
MEN LIKE?
YEAH. YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU REALLY NEED TO GET LAID.
OH, WELL, FOR YOUR
INFORMATION, DAISY...
[MIKE TURNS ON]I LOST MY VIRGINITY.
[PATRONS TITTERING]
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ YES, THAT'S WHAT
DONE HAPPENED TO ME ♪
♪ AND HE DON'T EVEN CALL
WHO WROTE THAT?
JANIS JOPLIN?
♪ NO, HE DON'T
♪ NOT AT ALL
♪ WHY WON'T HE
PICK UP THE PHONE ♪
♪ AND JUST CALL ME?
BOO!
SCREW THIS.
GEE, THANK YOU.
BLOODY HELL.
I'M GUESSING
YOU'RE AN ACTRESS.
UH-HUH.
AND I PRODUCE
A TV SHOW.
AND YOU'RE GOING TO
PUT ME ON IT
AND MAKE MY CAREER,
BLAH BLAH BLAH.
I'VE HEARD IT ALL.
YOU KNOW, DAISY,
YOU WANT TO BE
THE WORLD-WEARY INGENUE,
YOU GO FOR IT.
I'M SURE YOU
PLAY HER VERY WELL.
IT'S JUST NOT VERY
INTERESTING, YOU KNOW?
AT LEAST, NOT TO ME.
WELL, YOU'RE
INTERESTING TO ME.
YOU WANT TO GO
SOMEWHERE WITH ME?
I REALLY DO.
GEORGE, WILL YOU
SLOW DOWN?
I CAN'T KEEP UP.
THEY MOCK ME.
EVERYWHERE.
COUPLES MOCK ME.
YEAH, ME TOO, DARLING.
I'M SUCH AN IDIOT.
YOU KNOW,
I DON'T REMEMBER
THE FIRST TIME
I EVER DID IT. I DON'T.
I WAS DRINKING, A LOT,
AND I WOKE UP,
AND MY MATES TOLD ME
I WAS A MAN NOW,
AND I DON'T REMEMBER
A BLOODY THING.
AT LEAST YOU WERE
STILL ALIVE.
WELL, NOT FOR MUCH LONGER.
SO ANYWAY,
NOW MASON IS GOING
TO SHOW LITTLE GEORGIE
A FEW OF THE FINER POINTS
OF STRESS RELIEF
THROUGH PETTY VANDALISM.
OH, YES,
WE WILL EGG TRIP'S
FUCKING MANSION,
BUT FIRST...
YOU SEE,
THE PLEASURE COMES
FROM BEING A SHADOW
IN THE NIGHT, SILENT,
UNTIL THEY ARRIVE BACK
AT THEIR SMUG
LITTLE ESTABLISHMENT,
ONLY TO FIND A BIG--
GEORGE!
GEORGIE, I--
[ALARM RINGING]
I DON'T THINK I'VE
EXPLAINED TO YOU PROPERLY
THE, UH...
THE FINER DETAILS
OF THE "SHADOW IN THE NIGHT"
PHILOSOPHY, GEORGE.
SEE, UH, NOW IS
A GOOD TIME TO RUN AWAY.
GEORGIE...
[SIREN WAILING]
HELLO, OFFICER.
EVENING, MA'AM.
[GIRLS]
BEAT, BEAT, MUTILATE!
CRUSH, CRUSH, KILL!
YANK OUT THEIR ORGANS
AND THROW 'EM ON THE GRILL!
WHOO!
SETTLE DOWN, LADIES.
SORRY.
WE'RE SO SORRY.
READY?
[ALL] OKAY!
WE EAT SALAD,
WE STAY FIT!
NOT LIKE YOUR TEAM.
YOU EAT...
SHIFT TO THE LEFT,
SHIFT TO THE RIGHT,
STAND UP, SIT DOWN,
FIGHT, FIGHT, FIGHT!
WHOO!
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
IN FOR?
GRAND THEFT POM-POM?
TRY ASSAULT
AND BATTERY.
THEIR MASCOT TRIED
TO FUCK WITH OUR MASCOT.
YOU GOT TO DRAW THE LINE
SOMEWHERE.
IS THAT A FROG?
A FROG?
IT'S A SEA TURTLE.
SEA TURTLES...
[ALL] SNAP!
ROXY. FINALLY.
WHAT DID YOU DO?
I BROKE A WINDOW.
A REALLY BIG WINDOW.
IS THIS ABOUT A BOY?
I GUESS.
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU KNOW, GEORGE,
MEN HAVE MADE ME
ACT CRAZY TOO.
I MEAN, IF YOU
HAVEN'T BOUGHT
A GUN OR A PICK-AX
AT SOME POINT,
IT ISN'T
A REAL RELATIONSHIP.
THANK YOU, ROXY.
SO HERE'S WHAT
I'M GOING TO DO.
THANK GOD.
UNLOCK THIS THING.
YOUR ONE PHONE CALL.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
SURE YOU DO.
YOU WANT TO BE A GIRL
OR YOU WANT TO BE A WOMAN?
YOU CHOOSE.
IF YOU'RE YOUNG
AND NOT SO INNOCENT--
I MEAN, IF IT'S YOUR
FIRST TIME IN THE SLAMMER--
YOU CALL YOUR MOM.
SHE KNOWS EXACTLY WHAT TO SAY.
YOUR DAUGHTER'S
UPSTAIRS.
I KNOW.
WHO'S THIS?
OH, THAT'S...
THAT'S MY OTHER DAUGHTER.
I SHOULD HAVE SEEN THAT.
SHE'S PRETTY,
LIKE HER MOTHER.
THANK YOU.
WHAT'S HER NAME?
GEORGIA.
SO, UH...
SO WHAT ARE WE DOING?
ARE WE KISSING SOME MORE?
I THINK I SHOULD PROBABLY GO.
OKAY.
I HAD A REALLY
GREAT TIME, JOY.
ME TOO.
AND I LIKE KISSING YOU.
IT'S JUST...
I'M JUST NOT COMFORTABLE
WITH YOUR DAUGHTER
BEING SO CLOSE.
YEAH.
YOU'RE A REALLY
GOOD MAN, ANGELO.
[CHUCKLES]
YOU'RE SO CAREFUL
WITH PEOPLE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE
SO CAREFUL WITH ME.
I'LL CALL YOU.
OKAY.
OH, GOD, I THOUGHT YOU WERE
NEVER GOING TO GET HERE.
WHAT ARE YOU WEARING?
ONE OF US WAS ENJOYING
THE COMPANY OF A MAN
WHILE WATCHING
A LITTLE JOUSTING
THIS EVENING, MILLIE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
I DISTURBED THE PEACE.
BYE, BECKY,
BECKY, SHASTA.
IT'LL BE A FEW MINUTES
FOR THE PAPER, MA'AM.
MAKE SURE I GET
A 1035 ON THIS,
WILL YOU, OFFICER?
MILLIE, MILLIE, MILLIE.
I'M SORRY
I SCREWED UP YOUR DATE.
OH, IT'S OKAY.
THERE'S NO FUTURE
FOR A MAN
WHO CAN'T HOLD
HIS GROG, MILLIE.
THIS YOUR FIRST TIME?
YES,
AND THE ASSHOLE
NEVER EVEN CALLED.
YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT JAIL,
WEREN'T YOU?
MILLIE, SWEETHEART,
IT'S AN UNWRITTEN LAW.
THEY NEVER CALL
WHEN IT'S YOUR FIRST TIME.
WELL, IT STINKS.
THAT'S WHAT
FIRST TIMES ARE FOR,
AND NEXT TIME,
IT WON'T BE YOUR FIRST.
AND THAT'S WHAT
BEING ALIVE IS ALL ABOUT.
YEAH, I KNOW.
LOSING YOUR VIRGINITY
IS SUPPOSED TO BE
ONE OF THE STEPS
TOWARDS BEING REALLY ALIVE.
FOR ME,
IT WAS ONE OF THE WAYS
I FINALLY REALIZED
THAT IT WAS OVER.
YOU CAN'T UN-DO
WHAT YOU'VE DONE.
SOME THINGS YOU CAN'T CHANGE.
YOU CAN'T UN-SPILL WATER,
EVEN IF YOU WANT TO.
SOME CHOICES
YOU CAN LEARN TO LIVE WITH,
RIGHT THROUGH
TO THE CLEAR LIGHT OF MORNING.
THEY SAY COMING CLEAN
IS GOOD FOR THE SOUL,
THAT IT PUTS THINGS
IN PERSPECTIVE.
YOU CAN GET A SENSE
OF YOUR PLACE
IN THE ORDER OF THINGS...
A SENSE OF WHO YOU REALLY ARE
AND WHAT'S IMPORTANT.
THIS IS MY PERSPECTIVE.
I AM A GRIM REAPER.
I TAKE SOULS.
I DO NOT GO TO PROM.
I DO NOT LIVE
HAPPILY EVER AFTER.
THIS IS WHO I AM.
ANYONE GOT
A PROBLEM WITH THAT?