[GEORGE]:  Everybody dies.
That's just the way it is.
I'm told I'm not
supposed to argue
or question or even
try to understand.
I'm told a lot these days,
ever since my
life was snuffed out
by a toilet seat,
and I joined
the ranks of the undead.
You, little dead girl,
are gonna be a grim reaper.
My name is George Lass.
I take souls for a living.
This is Rube.
He's undead, too.
He's the one
who gets the list,
who's to die, when and where,
which he passes on
to the rest of
us grim reapers.
[GEORGE]: ETD?
Estimated time of death.
[GEORGE]:  Do you guys
get off dropping
pianos on people?
[RUBE]:  It's not our
job to drop the pianos
or the toilet seats.
Whose job is it?
[RUBE]: Gravelings.
[GEORGE]:  Reapers don't get
a free ride.
What are you doing?
Collecting my salary.
We don't get paid,
like, through proper channels?
Hi.
I'm Delores Herbig, as in...
"Her big brown eyes."
What kind of universe
would give me the power
to extract souls
from people's bodies,
but still force me
to keep a suck-ass job
if I want to eat?
This was my home.
And this was my family.
They're having trouble coping.
[JOY]:  Keeping a dead
animal in your toy box
is something
a crazy person would do.
I'm not crazy.
[GEORGE]:  I was having
trouble coping, too.
I don't think I'm
supposed to be doing this.
[RUBE]: You're learning.
You gotta think
about all the things you like
and decide whether
they're worth
sticking around for.
And if they are,
you'll find a way to do this.
[GEORGE]:  What if I don't?
[RUBE]:  Then you go away.
[GEORGE]:  When I was alive,
I never looked
at the obituaries,
like, not even once.
Now I read them first,
the reaper's sports pages.
And every time I
see someone who lived
to even 50,
it kind of annoys me.
Was your name
ever in the paper?
[SIGHS] Constantly. I still
have all the clippings.
I made the police reports
a couple of times, you know.
"Unidentified male,
slender build,
seen fleeing the premises."
That kind of thing.
That doesn't count.
How about you, sweetie?
Mmm! Do tell.
"Teen Killed by Falling Debris
from Space Station."
Technically,
that was the day
after your life.
[MASON]: My demise
went unreported.
Drug-related
deaths in the '60s
were very common.
I've got to go wee-wee.
[GEORGE]:
Was your death reported?
Oh, please.
I perished in a huge fire
on the set of
Gone with the Wind.
Not a word, huh?
Nothing. The story was buried.
And three days later...So were you.
But my picture
was in the paper
a whole lot before I died.
Why?
On the arm of
whatever famous man
I was sleeping with.
Mmm... Right. Not my thing.
You never slept with anybody?
No.
Why didn't you?
Well, Daisy, first of all,
I was 18 years old.
Not a great excuse.
I never had a boyfriend.
[DAISY]: Not really a problem.
[GEORGE]: I lived at home
with my parents
and little sister.
Ever heard of a car?
Is it just my imagination
or have I become
much more attractive
since I've laid
off the booze and,
you know, whatnot?
Your breath is better.
Your eyes are less puffy.
And you don't have as much
drool around your mouth,
which is nice.
You know,
the most
attractive thing about you
when you were
drinking and whatnot
is that you really had no idea
if you were attractive.
'Cause when people know
they're attractive,
they're not.
And it's not about
what's on the outside.
It's not about this.
It's about this.
It's about what's in here.
Then he's a very
handsome man.[GEORGE]: Hmm.
But am I pretty?
Oh, you're darling.
You make my heart flutter.
Mine, too.
Really?No.
There's souls to
be taken, folks,
this morning before breakfast.
One, two, three, four, five.
Why do I only get one?
Because three doesn't
go into five evenly.
What does Roxy get?
Uh, usually eggs.
Side of fruit?
I was thinking
hash browns today.
Nice.
These are all at
the farmer's market,
in exactly 27 minutes.
I smell a disaster.[SCOFFS]
No, five deaths
is not a disaster.
How many deaths is a disaster?
More than five.
Five's bullshit.
How many?
Sixteen to 20, disaster.
Twenty-one and up,
catastrophe.
Eight to 15 is a calamity.
Seven and under?That's a crying shame.
Pick me up some
heirloom tomatoes
while you're out there?
[GEORGE]: Sure.
[MASON]: See you later.[DAISY]: Goodbye.
Anything in the paper?
Two heart
attacks and a stroke.
Nice.
[GEORGE]:  Trying to
find your reap is kind of like
a game of
hide-and-go-seek,
except when I find you,
when I put the tag on you,
you're out for good.
Ready or not, you're dead.
Okay, enough with the game.
I haven't had breakfast
and Mama wants a waffle.
Come out,
come out, wherever you are.
Oh, we have a winner.
Thanks, boys.
This has been a treat.
Ooh!
Ooh! I'm done.
Two of the hard hats get it.
Want to get a latte?
No, you've got to go.
I've got something to do.
It's been two hours now, guys.
I still smell propane.
This is killing my business.
I'm usually swamped by 9:00.
[GEORGE]:
Today you're toe-up by 10:00.
Do you think Eliza Doolittle
had to put up
with this nonsense?
Who?Audrey Hepburn, sweetheart.
Yeah, and look at me,
still waiting
for Rex Harrison.
[WORKER]: Don't hold your
fucking breath.
You see, this is
who I sell flowers to.
Men who need to apologize
for the things
they say to women.
He'll end up paying
for it one way or other.
Pink lilies.
On the house.
My first customer of the day.
[GEORGE]:  Oh, great.
She can see the guilt
written all over me.
Mine, too.
I couldn't find it.
Jeez, you people
can find Pearl Harbor
in the middle of the night,
you can't find a gas leak.
I'm Chinese, cocksucker.
[GROWLING]
[GEORGE]:  Gravelings.
Fucking troublemakers.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[GEORGE]:  Bodies everywhere.
And a dead flower
girl in the middle.
It was like
a really fucked up wedding.
She gave me a pretty flower,
and what did I give her?
Nothing.
I took her soul.
I don't know why
but I felt like I
had betrayed her.
Or someone.
The last time I had
seen a death like this
was my own
and I wanted to run away
as fast as I could.
[BELL DINGING]
[MAN]: Order up.
Do you know what I love best
about being sober?
Not waking up
in a pool of your own vomit?
Definitely that, yeah.
But, no,
it's the taste of food.
[MIMICS CHOMPING]
I mean, after all these years,
I finally realize
why you guys eat here,
in Der fucking Waffle Haus.
[RUBE]: This is a wise move.
Bacchus has
drowned many more men
than Neptune.
Bacchus? What?
He's the Greek god of
Why-Don't-You-
Read-A-Fucking-Book?
[MASON]: Oh.
When did you die?
1960-something?
'66.
Taking every
nasty-ass drug you could get
your nasty-ass
paws on for 40 years.
Yeah.
Oh, no, no, not everything,
because I was always
deathly afraid of needles,
and I still am.
They've made great strides
in the design of needles.
They're sharper.
Sharper?
Sharper is less painful.
Are you going to finish
those hash browns?
Probably not.
Mmm!
Fucking bloody hell!
I'm out of here.
Did you see that?
I mean, just because I wanted
some of her hash browns.
I was there.
I've never seen such violence
over such small potatoes.
Now, that was almost clever.
What was almost clever, Rube?
The thing about
the hash browns
being small potatoes.
I don't get it.
Because hash browns
are small potatoes.
Never mind.
Daisy.Roxy.
This weather
kind of suits you.
Oh, you know, Roxy,
I really don't think it does.
Off to work you go.
[SCOFFS]
[SIGHS]
Why do I even bother with you?
Because I'm one
of the few fools
who gets you.
Really? Well, what do you get?
When I go to
the pound to pick up a dog
I don't take
the one that wags its tail
and licks my face
and jumps all over me.
I pick the one in the corner,
alone, shaking.
Well, go on,
get inside where it's warm.
Go, girl.Okay.
There you go. There you go.
Daisy Adair.
Chihuahua.
Hello?
Is anyone here?
Reggie?
[SIGHS]
You know,
when someone calls your name,
you could say, "Hi. I'm here.
What's up, Mom?" All right?
A simple "What is it?"
would suffice.
What is it?
[SIGHS]
This is how we're gonna spend
your school holiday?
Looks that way.
All right.
I just saw Bridget and Annie
heading down to the park.
Why don't you go
catch up with them?
I don't think so.
Give me one good reason.
I don't really
like getting baked
before noon.
Baked?
Oh.
Reggie, I'm not going to...
I don't. I haven't. I won't.
Did you ever catch
your sister doing stuff?
No. Did you?
No. Never.
I don't think your
sister smoked pot.
I searched constantly.
No, all George ever did was...
Pretty much what
you're doing now.
Whatever, Mom.
Your father and I
have another
doctor's appointment.
Stay out of the park.
And I'd better not see
any cherry stains
on those cushions.
It's not a real doctor.
It's a shrink.
[J.D. BARKS]
[GEORGE]:  Rube didn't want me
lurking around my old house.
He didn't want me
spying on my family.
He said that
a reaper should be
like a soldier in a foxhole.
Lay low, don't be a hero,
don't take any
unnecessary risks.
What's the point
of keeping your head down
once it's
already been blown off?
How'd it go this morning?
Oh, real fun.
Try to get me
another one like that
real soon.
How about a little breakfast?
I'll have
the Johnny Vegas over easy
and a small grapefruit juice.
You could hear the explosion
all the way over here.
The Johnny Vegas
comes with a side...
It was disgusting.
Her body was blown to pieces.
Her brain was...
Cottage cheese. Yeah.
Pretty flower.
Did someone betray you?
What?
Did some guy screw you over?
[RUBE]: I thought we had
decided that you
and romantic
entanglements were...
It's not a good idea.
And I thought
George was a virgin.
What? No. No. No guy.
And who told you
that I was a virgin?
Did you tell him that?
No.She did.
It's just a flower. Fuck!
Well, I only got flowers
when somebody betrayed me.
Well, I didn't betray anyone.
She didn't say you did.
[EXCLAIMS DISGUSTEDLY]
It tastes like ass. Try that.
I'm trying to stay off
the arse juice for now
but, you know, thank you.
Do you know who
sent beautiful flowers?
French tulips?
I'll just give
you his initials.
Douglas Fairbanks, Jr.
Errol Flynn,
all that money, carnations.
[RUBE]: I cannot sit here
and listen to more
witless stories
about star fucking.
You and you. Let's go.
Rube, sorry,
but I've got to
finish Roxy's breakfast.
Well, here.
Why don't you take it to go?
It's a disgusting habit,
eating off someone's plate.
If you want to be
an ex-drug addict,
why don't you
behave like one, huh?
[CHUCKLES]
Crazy fucking fuck.
Oh, how I wish the words
would roll off my tongue
as they do yours.
[GRUNTS]
[DAISY]: [SIGHS] Another
outdoor death. My lips
are getting so chapped.
Roxy says I look like a dog.
I didn't betray anyone.
Do I look like
some kind of stray
that needs to be saved?
I'm really pretty,
don't you think?
Mmm-hmm.
I need verbal reassurance.
You're not a dog.
No, say the thing.
You're really pretty.
Say the whole thing.
You're the most
exquisite beauty
the world has ever seen.
I've got to go.
What about your breakfast?
I don't want it.
You forgot your flower.
[GEORGE]:  I did want it.
I just didn't feel
like carrying around
the reminder of
my morning death
the rest of my day.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Hi, Crystal.
Which is why
it wasn't so bad
walking into Happy Time.
Where the only
thing ever written
on a Post-it Note
was stuff like...[FARTING]
"Who farted?"
And "10 copies, A.S.A.P."
And "Please see me."
Oh, Millie.Delores.
I've got news.
Bad news.
I have to hire
my boss's nephew.
I'm sorry, Millie,
but this boy, Brennan,
has had a world of
trouble finding a job...
What, you're firing me?
You're shit-canning
me just like that?
No. Why would you think that?
"Bad news," "boss's nephew,"
seemed where you were headed.
I want you to
train him, Millie,
and I don't care
for the language.
Although I do kind
of like that phrase.
Shit-can. Shit-can.
That's the bad news?
I have to train someone?
No, the bad news is
he's dumb as a bag of hammers.[GROANS]
I'm starting him on reception.
Just show him
the phone system.
I'd ask Crystal
but she's not a people person.
No more trainees, Delores.
I can't take it.
[KNOCKING]
Yeah?Hi.
The phone's not working.
Dial nine first.
I'm Brennan.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm training you.
Sweet.
Should I go do it now?
No time like the present.
Go. Oh, Millie?
I would never shit-can you.
You're very special to me.
Come here.
I can't send you
out into the world
with schmutz all
over your face.
Oh, go. Stop. Go.
[GEORGE]:  You had to wonder
about Delores Herbig
and her big, strange heart.
You had to
wonder about how long
that schmutz had
been on my face.
Is it "schmootz" or "schmutz"?
So, how was your week?
It was good.
I think we had a good week.
Joy?
Well, I find myself
getting really disgusted
when he eats.
I mean, physically sick.
That's nice.
I think
the walls of his cheeks
have gotten too thin
as he's gotten older
because you can
hear the crunching
and the spit and
the swallowing.
I swear to God,
when he's eating a salad,
I want to take my own life.
I'm standing in
a grocery store
the other day,
and I'm holding
a head of iceberg lettuce
and I just can't even
buy the fucking thing.
What would you
like me to do, Joy?
Be nice if you
ate in the kitchen
with the dog.
At least he's capable of love.
J.D. doesn't love you.
You give him meat.
At least one of
us is getting it.
Okay,
I think for this to work,
you two need to be
a little less
honest with each another.
We actually had
that in our vows,
but we just took that
out at the last minute.
You've been married
for over 20 years.
Things have happened,
and you know that
things have happened.
Like when he
started banging someone
in one of his
Shakespeare classes.
That kind of thing?
You know, Joy,
if maybe you could stop
wisecracking
for two seconds...
Did you hear that?
"Wisecracking."
I'm sorry,
who talks like that?
For a marriage to work
you have to
conspire with your partner
to not say everything.
You know things aren't perfect
and you don't
hammer away at it
out of respect
for the marriage.
For a marriage to work,
you and your husband
have to be in cahoots.
In cahoots?
Marriage is
a silent conspiracy
between two people to not
confess everything.
To let sleeping dogs lie.
I like that.
[CHUCKLES WRYLY]
Oh, I bet you do.
And that's worked
for your marriage?
I think it has.
My wife and I,
we've been in
cahoots for 10 years.
So does that mean
she does or doesn't
know that you're gay?
[STUTTERING]
She probably knows.
[ALL CLAMORING]
[CONRAD]:
Meter people, meter people.
Let's settle down.
All right, all right.
Item one.
Chuck's
Charbroiler on Mandeville
is starting
a lunch special today.
Burger, fries and soda
for 59 cents.
Those of you
working Mandeville
and its environs,
expect a three-light back up
and plenty of
red-zone violations.
Fifty-nine cents for a burger.
What's in it?
German Shepherd on
a sesame-seed bun?
[ALL LAUGHING][CONRAD]: Moving on.
We've received complaints
from some of the citizenry
about inappropriate language,
aggressive behavior,
and in one instance,
that a member of this corps
pulled a firearm.
People, in a world of
increasing hostility,
your job,
as always, is to placate.
To meet anger with stoicism.
In short,
no more mouthing off.
If you cannot do that,
if you cannot
hold your tongue,
then you should seek
another line of work.
Okay, let's roll.
[ALL SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
And people, people!
Let's be careful out there.
[HORN HONKING]
Okay, so if you
want to dial someone
in the office, you...
[STAMMERING]
I totally know this one.
[GEORGE]:  Look at those lips.
[GROWLS]
I just want to bite your face.
You dial their
extension first?
I want to tear your
skin off,
make pajamas out of them,
and wear them to bed.
Excellent.
[PHONE RINGING]
Should I answer it?
[WHISPERING]
Let's give that a whirl.
Okay.
Happy Time. Millie's phone.
This is Brennan.
Good stuff.It's for you.
Ask who it is.Oh.
Uh, who is it?
Daisy, Daisy Adair.
Hi, Daisy.
Yeah,
Millie's training me, yeah.
She's awesome.
She's got
the most beautiful eyes.
[PHONE RINGING]
Uh... Um, what do I do?
Put Daisy,
Daisy Adair, on hold.
Oh, okay.[PHONES RINGING]
You should probably ask Daisy
to hold first.
Hello?
Okay, click over.
Click what back over?
That, that... Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Okay, they'll call back.
[EXHALES]
Do you want to
hang out tonight?
Yes.
[RUBE]:
You know I don't do kids.
This is your Post-it.
[MASON]:
Look, please just help me
find L. Sondheim,
and you can go.
Cecil!Ugh!
I want to strangle him,
I really do.
I just want to kill him.
Yeah?
Is your name L. Sondheim,
by any chance?
No.
Come on.
There'll be little cupcakes
with little sprinkles on them.
Ten minutes.
Here, come on, buddy.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go. There you go.
Have a good time.
Cecil. Cecil!
Can I help you?
Yeah. We're, uh... We're here
for, you know,
the little kids' party.
Please tell me
you're from the clown service.
We're from the clown service.
Lloyd,
the clown finally showed up.
Okay, which one of
you is the clown?
Oh, I think
it's pretty obvious.
Okay, so you see the frail,
indecisive looking
man in the plaid shirt?
That's my husband.
He's got your money.
Go, go, go. You were supposed
to be in costume
20 minutes ago.
One minute, please.
I really hate clowns.
When I was five years old,
I kicked one in the nuts.
That man over there
wants to give you some money.
But if one little kid
were to take a poke at me,
I will punch it back.
I swear to God,
I will kick its
little fucking teeth out.
[SING-SONG VOICE] Coming![CHUCKLES]
He's not one of those angry
alcoholic clowns, is he?
Oh, no. Actually,
he just swore off booze.
It's strictly seltzer water
the last three weeks.
All that seltzer water
would make any
clown a little angry.
I don't get it.There's nothing to get.
[GEORGE]:  You cannot go out
with this Brennan guy.
It would never work.
You're a Taurus.
He's a Gemini.
He's Lutheran. You're dead.
You have to weasel
your way out of this.
You have to tell him, "No."
Oh, my God.
Some slut is
stealing my boyfriend.
Millie.
Come, come, come.
How'd you like to be in charge
of another special project?
As in training someone else
with special needs?
Oh, how did it go with Brennan
and the phone system?
He went a little ADD on me
when I tried to show him
how to use the speakerphone.
This afternoon
we're gonna try
transferring calls.
You seem a little distracted.
[GASPS] Oh, Fran!
Have you no shame?
Please tell me you
don't have a crush
on that simple boy.
I don't. Just give me
the project, Delores.
These are top-secret files.
Shred them.
Got it.
They sleep with the fishes.
You know, office
romances never end well.
When Julio
empties my trash basket
he can barely
make eye contact.
Uh, that's...upsetting.
And that boy here...
[SIGHS] I know. I know.
Look, you are still a baby.
You have your
whole life ahead of you
to find the right person.
Something that'll really last.
[CHUCKLING]
[GEORGE]:  I'm a virgin with
a death certificate.
What the fuck
am I waiting for?
[CLANCY]: The sound of
my eating makes you
physically sick?
Oh, yeah. That's right.
You save your best
shots for an audience.
[JOY]: You know what, Clancy?
You don't have to
listen to it every night.
You know what, Joy?
You don't have to
listen to it at all.
listen to it ever again.
What does that mean?
Joy? Do you want
to be married to me?
I don't.
[GEORGE]:  Waiting for
the right boy to come along.
Right, Delores.
And although my body
had been declared dead,
it hadn't gone cold.
Ah, fuck! Fuck me!
What happened?
Oh, it's nothing,
it's just a cut. I'm fine.
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]Are you okay?
Yeah.
Oh, hey.
I actually am
feeling a little woozy.
Okay.
I'll get you some water.
There you go, Emily.
This isn't a bunny rabbit.
Yes, it is.
Look. There are the ears.
What is it, really?
Go ask your mother.
I want a bunny rabbit
balloon like Emily's.
I bet you do, sweetheart.
Clowns aren't
supposed to talk.
Yes, they are. Clowns talk.
Don't they?
It's mimes that are silent.
Clowns can
definitely fucking talk,
all right?
No, not true.
Some clowns talk.
Some make honking noises.
Do me a favor.
Get me a piece of cake.
I want a bunny rabbit balloon.
When I see some cake.
You get a move on.
Please don't hump
me on the frosting.
Stupid.
Hey. Can I talk to
you for a second?
Yeah.
Bloody hell!
This is my kid's party.
And this,
this isn't a bunny rabbit.
Yeah, sorry, Mr...
Sondheim.
Lloyd.
Look,
don't you have other stuff
you can do?
Any magic tricks?
Yeah, I've got one or two.
Well, use them.
This is
the only sixth birthday
my daughter will ever have.
Here, drink some more water.
[GEORGE]:  I don't know
why I liked him.
Maybe just because
that slut Fran did.
But I think it
had something to do
with my death this morning.
I couldn't get that
strange pink flower
out of my head.
I felt as if something
was hanging by a thread,
not just my finger,
and I had to try
to hold onto it.
Have another sip.
I feel better.
What, are you
following me, blondie?
Don't flatter yourself.
I have a Post-it.
C. Sullivan?
Luck of the Irish.
$35?
Greedy fucking Americans.
I put a curse on you.
May you never walk the Earth
in happiness again.
Sir, that voodoo shit don't
play with me, c omprende?
Fuck you, piece of
shit little meter maid.
May hair grow on your balls.
Let's go.
Bring it on. Gloves off.
Boss man says I can't.
I can't mouth off.
Roxy can't mouth off?
You're like
a bird without a song.
A really mean bird.
Roxy?
Why would you say
I look like a dog
who needed to be
saved from the pound?
[SIGHS]
Don't do this to me, Daisy.
I'm just tired.
I didn't sleep well.
I had a bad dream.
[ROXY]: Flying, swimming,
or running from monsters,
it all means the same thing,
no Pop-Tarts after 10:00.[BOYS SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
It was my first day
on the set of
Gone With The Wind...
And you die.
I know that story.
No,
in my dream I'm about to meet
one of my idols, Vivien Leigh.
I've dreamt about
it my whole life.
I was really worried,
you know,
what if we don't get along?
What if she hates me?
Worse yet,
what if she ignores me?
That'll teach them
to mess with
Catherine Sullivan.
But in my dream,
it's wonderful.
She runs through
her whole,
"As God is my witness,
I'll never be hungry again,"
and I tell her it's
a touch over the top,
and she says I'm right,
and we just gossip
and giggle like
long-lost sisters.
[BOY]: She took my money.
She took my wallet, dude.
[GRUNTS]
So, that's why
I was a little out
of it this morning.
It was a rough dream.
What is so rough
about that dream?
It never happened.
I died before I met her.
Shut up out there!
I'll only be a minute!
[SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[CHILDREN SCREAMING]
Bloody hell.
I do believe that
is the Chinese symbol
for "aim here."
Wow.
I find that comment
vile and contemptible.
Now say you're sorry.
I'm sorry, Rube.
I'm sorry you're 100 years old
and will never
get to spank that.
[IMITATES HONKING]
Make a funny face.No.
Go away.
Give the kid a face.
It's her birthday.
[SPEAKING GIBBERISH]
He's funny.
[RUBE]: Yes, he is.
Are you the clown's daddy?[SNORTS]
No.
Then why are you here?
I am somebody's daddy.
She's just not at this party.
Then where is she?
Why don't you play
with the clown, sweetheart?
I want you to remember
how funny he was, okay?
Hey.
[SPEAKING GIBBERISH]
[GIGGLING]
[MIMICS HONKING]
[GEORGE]:  My day had
started with a death.
The first sign of
trouble was all those
bright orange pylons
around the gas leak.
You put them up when you want
to keep people at a distance.
There was blood everywhere.
[GEORGE]:  That's what I
needed now. Lots and lots
of orange pylons.
How'd it go?
How did what go?
Making out with Brennan?
Severing my middle finger?
Putting it back
on without letting
everyone know
I was a grim reaper?
It went well.
I heard you cut yourself.
It's nothing.
You just need to take
better care of yourself,
Millie.
The world is
a dangerous place.
It's an easy
place for a young girl
to get hurt.
I'm fine.
I think I'm gonna
pull you off Brennan.
Well, I was never really
on Brennan.
You're smart, you're charming,
you're a very
complicated young woman,
and I just don't
like to see your talents
wasted on
projects like Brennan.
What are we talking about?
We're talking
about a promotion,
you silly goose.
We are?Well, I think we are.
Two more days a week,
and $200 more a week.
You're shitting me!
Your new
position at Happy Time
will be to
interview potential temps.
We're frittering
away your talents
in data entry and
training boys like Brennan.
That's a waste of your time.
Do we understand each other?
I won't let you down.
I can't believe that.
What a joke.
Since I just got promoted,
I just thought
you two should know
that I take my
coffee with a little milk,
two sugars, and a lot
less of your bullshit.
God, I hate her.
What a little bitch.
[GEORGE]:  Don't even turn to
see the wreckage.
Can you
describe the other kid?
[CHATTERING IN
FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
What the hell?
The other kid
was a little taller
than this one,
slender build, baggy jeans.
He had on a black sweatshirt
with some yin-yang
bull on the back of it,
and then he headed
north down Marine.
He was pretty
banged up, too, probably.
What's your name?
Roxy.
You the one who
clotheslined this kid?
Mmm-hmm.
I like your style.
You got the wrong job, Roxy.
I ain't got
nothing but wrong jobs.
So, do you guys just, like,
hate each other's guts?
No, your mother and I
don't hate each other.
We love each other very much.
We just...
We just can't live together.
But we both love you,
and even though
other things will change,
that won't.
[CLANCY]: You know, Reg,
it's okay to feel
whatever you're feeling.
I mean, don't be
afraid to have feelings.
What are your feelings,
sweetheart?
I'm a little hungry.
So, which one of
you gets, you know...
Well, your mother and I
haven't exactly
worked that out yet.
I know your mom
wants you to...
Who gets J.D.?
[JOY]: Well, sweetheart, J.D.
is your dog.
But I'm sure if you
want to
lend him to your dad
every now and then, you know,
I'm sure he'd appreciate it.
[REGGIE]: Tisha Cotter's
parents got a divorce
and her dad got this
really cheesy condo.
Shag carpeting and
mirrors everywhere.
Well, I'm not gonna get
a cheesy condo, Reggie.
Well, you have to get
a backyard. For J.D.
We'll see, sweetie.
Most sorority houses
do come with backyards.
You just can't leave it alone.
You just can't help yourself.
Oh, that's great.
I can't help myself.
I can't...
You've been tapping little
Miss Kappa Kappa Gamma's
keg for a year now.
[CLANCY]: You know,
did it ever occur to you
that maybe you pushed me
in that direction?
Oh, really?
That's... Boy, poor you.
Please enlighten me.
[CLANCY]: It's the same way
that you drive
everyone around you away.
You did the same
thing to George.
You wanted her
out of this house.
You wanted her gone
and now she's gone.
[JOY]: Get out. Get out!
Get out of this
house right now
or I will scream!
[GEORGE]:  My parents took
me and my little sister
to the circus every year.
I liked
the trapeze artists the best,
The Flying Wallendas
or whatever they were called.
Not the death-defying stuff,
the mid-air quadruple flips
and near-misses.
I covered my eyes for that.
What I liked was
the part at the end
when they bounced
into the net
and jumped up with that
big Wallenda smile.
The "ta-dah" part.
Ta-dah. I loved that.
It meant "I'm safe."
Hi.
I can't go out
with you tonight.
Okay.
Uh, maybe some other time.
I don't... I don't know.
Oh, okay.
Well, that's cool, you know?
Just hang onto
my phone number.
Okay.
Hopefully I'll see you around
sometime or something.
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY] Well,
we work in the same office.
Yeah.
Does it hurt?
Your... Your finger?
The cut you...
Oh, no.
Oh, good, good. I'm glad.
Thank you.
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
[WHISPERS] Ta-dah.
That was the thing
with the Wallendas,
why I always covered my eyes
until it was over.
Eventually,
one of them's gotta fall.
[CHILDREN YELLING]
Daddy, it's not breaking.
I know, sweetheart.
Hey, Eddie, finish this.
Oh, man.
Try not to kill anyone.
[EXCLAIMS]
[CHILDREN LAUGHING]
Daddy, Daddy.
It's still not breaking.
Sweetie, the pinata's
going to crack open.
You'll get your candy.
Has Daddy ever
let you down before?
No.
Sorry.
I'll bring it right back.
[SIGHS]
Knock it out.
[CHILDREN YELLING]
[GAGGING]
Am I dead?
Yeah. Yeah, you're dead.
Who are you?
Me? Mason.
You're not the clown?
[CHUCKLING]
No, I'm not the fucking clown.
What were you doing here?
Well, I was...
I took your soul
before you, you know...
And now I'm
supposed to escort you
to your lights.
No, what were you doing?
You made obscene
balloon animals
for my daughter.
You insulted all my guests,
and the whole time
you knew I was gonna die?
Is this a joke?
This is how she'll
remember her birthday?
Do you want to come with me?
I'm gonna take you
to your lights...
Stay away from me.
Stay away from my family.
Just... Just go.
[GEORGE]:  Life always seemed
to be about two things,
feeling bad
and then feeling better.
For me,
the feeling bad
part came pretty easy.
But the feeling better part,
how to make
myself feel better,
I never got that part down.
[LEAD SNAPS][GROANS]
These No. 2 soft always break.
I keep telling you
to buy the No. 4s,
but you don't listen.
What's with the sad face?
Some sad story.
Rent's due,
job sucks, cat's pregnant.
You haven't seen
Mason lately, have you?
Kiffany, can I get
some coffee, please?
Why do you drink
coffee so late?
You don't sleep as it is.
Make that an espresso.
Thank you.
Little Miss Cranky Pants.
Whatever oats
you're sowing at this moment,
whatever need you feel
to make some
kind of a statement
or question my authority...
Is it something I did?
Nothing's wrong.
I got a promotion.
What kind of
promotion did you get?
Two more big bills
a week. Hunge.Huh.
I joined the Police Academy.
No, you didn't.
[RUBE]: Yes, she did.
They want more days,
these Happy Time people?
I think you should
decline the offer.
Fuck that.
It's done. I'm doing it.
Roxy,
give us a moment, will you?
Why can't I do this?
I'm doing this.
She's joining
the fucking Police Academy.
Roxy is not your concern.
I'm just worried
that you're
taking on too much.
People love to take roses
and they forget
about the thorns.
[SIGHS] Okay,
now, that's really beautiful,
but I'm taking the promotion.
Uh-uh. I wouldn't do that.
What did she do now?
Nice cross.
Have any trouble
getting the blood off?
[DAISY]: No,
just soap and water.
[RUBE]: I just think
you should go in there
tomorrow morning
and tell that Delores woman,
"Thank you, but no."
I want to do this.
I want more money.
"I want, I want."
Look, Peanut...
Don't call me that.
I just think all that wanting
is not so good at this point,
and that's all I have to say
about your promotion.
Well, as much
as I've enjoyed
this little pow-wow,
I think I'm just going to do
what I'm going to do.
[KIFFANY]: Miss,
your espresso?
I don't want it.
We made it.
Somebody's got to pay for it.
She's a cop.
Don't they get
everything for free?
[KIFFANY]: I thought
you were a meter maid.
[ROXY]: Well, I'm a cop now.
Good for you, baby.
Coffee's free for cops.
Un-fucking-real.
What do you mean,
you're a cop?
I joined the Police
Academy this afternoon.
Yeah, I don't
think I care for that.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[FROG CROAKING]
Hey, there, Mr. Frog.
How was your day?
Mine was fucked up.
My flower.
I thought you might want it.
So, who was that boy
on the phone today?
"Brendan."
Brennan.
Who's Brennan,
who thinks you
have beautiful eyes?
Nobody.
Okay, I kissed him.
And?"And?"
What was the kiss like?
It's not too late to
call him, you know.
I'm not gonna call him.
Delores doesn't want
me getting involved
with anyone at Happy Time.
Besides, he's not my type.
Not even close.
He's a pretty boy.
That's obvious.
Go to bed, Daisy.
So, Rube doesn't
want you at Happy Time.
That makes you unhappy.
Delores wants
you at Happy Time
but just so long
as you're unhappy.
It just sounds like a plan.
Life sucks, and then you die,
and then it still sucks.
What's with the cross?
I don't know. I like it.
What are you,
like, Catholic now?
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Yeah, why not?
Good for you.
You're so angry.And you're not?
Listen to me.
I died in 1938,
and there's not
a day that goes by
that I don't wonder
about the things I did
and the things I didn't do...
I know, and you were
going to be a great actress,
and you were
beautiful and talented
and you slept with all the men
under the moon.
Stop making fun of me.
Just shut up for once.
You think you know everything.
Look how unhappy you are.
I'm sorry you were so young
when you died, Georgia.
Good night.
[GEORGE]:  I knew who that
pink flower was for.
I knew who I'd betrayed.
My short life was
like our family outings
to the circus.
It wasn't so bad,
a bit with a clown,
some cotton candy...
And just as
things got interesting,
I covered my eyes.
I know what
that Wallenda smile
at the end was about.
Why they were so happy
with their mid-air
flips and near-misses.
They were happy because
they were brave
enough to be themselves.
I mean, if you're a Wallenda,
you have to
climb up that ladder.
You have to grab
that trapeze bar.
If you're a Wallenda
you have to jump off,
eyes wide open.