[ ♪♪]
WHEN I WAS LITTLE, MY FATHER,
WHO WAS AN ENGLISH TEACHER,
USED TO TELL ME
THAT I WOULD NEVER BE ALONE
AS LONG AS I HAD A GOOD BOOK.
GOOD THING.
YOU READY TO GO
TO SUSIE'S BIRTHDAY PARTY?
NO. MY BOOK'S GETTING GOOD.
GEORGE, WE RSVP'd.
I DIDN'T RSVP ANYTHING.
WE BOUGHT HER A PRESENT.
WHAT DID YOU GET HER?
WE GOT HER
A FLANNEL NIGHTGOWN,
WITH PRETTY LITTLE
FLOWERS ON IT.
MOM, YOU'RE GOING TO
GET ME KILLED.
GEORGIA, DON'T BE SILLY.
WE'RE GOING.
NOT.YOU ARE SO.
SO NOT.WHY DO YOU HAVE TO BE
SO OBSTINATE?
"OBSTINATE."
O-B-S-T...
I-N-A-T-E.
"STUBBORN."
GEORGIA LASS,
YOU CANNOT SPEND
YOUR ENTIRE LIFE
WITH YOUR NOSE
STUCK IN A BOOK.
TRY ME.
READING DIDN'T
MAKE ME POPULAR,
AND READING DIDN'T
NECESSARILY MAKE ME HAPPY.
WHAT IT DID MAKE ME
WAS A REALLY GOOD SPELLER.
"SUCCEDANEUM."
S-U-C-C-E-D-A-N-E-U-M.
FUCK OFF.
S... U...
C-C-E-D...
A-N-E-U-M.
NICE ONE, GEORGIE.
I WAS A READER.
FOCUS, HARJEET.
EYES ON THE PRIZE.
YOUR TROPHY,
AND 10,000 BIG ONES!
MR. AKHTAR, NO TALKING
TO THE FINALISTS.
I'M GUNNING FOR THE NERD.
AND THAT WOULD BE WHICH ONE?
"THANATOS."
[ WHISPERING ]: SHIT.
COULD I HEAR
THE DEFINITION, PLEASE?
DESIRE FOR DEATH.
"AN INSTINCTUAL DESIRE
FOR DEATH."
VERY NICE, MASON.
IT IS KIND OF
IN MY WHEELHOUSE,
ISN'T IT?
COME ON, FRANCIS.
KICK HIS LITTLE ASS.
GO ON, MY SON.
GO ON.
UH, SHOULDN'T YOU BE
FOCUSING ON THAT?
UH, SHOULDN'T YOU
SHUT THE FUCK UP
SO HE CAN SPELL
THE FUCKING WORD, GEORGIE?
"THANATOS."
T-H...
A-N...
A...
T-O-S.
"THANATOS."
EXCUSE ME.
MR. McFADDEN.
THAT WORD IS
FAR TOO EASY.
THAT'S YOUR GUY.IT'S AN INSULT.
MY SON HAS HAD
MUCH HARDER WORDS.
MUCH HARDER.
PLEASE REMAIN SILENT,
OR YOU WILL BE ASKED
TO LEAVE THE AUDITORIUM.
THE NEXT WORD IS...
"APOPLECTIC."
MISS IT.MISS IT.
MISS IT.
GAME OVER ANYWAY.
"APOPLECTIC."
A-P...
P-E-P...
L-E-C-T-I-C.
"APOPLECTIC."
I'M SORRY.
"APOPLECTIC" IS SPELLED
A-P--
NO!
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
OH, I'M AFRAID
YOU ARE D-E...
D.THAT'S D-E-A-D.
I WAS JOKING.
COFFEE, PLEASE, KIFFANY.
DOES ANYONE EVER ORDER
THE ELVIS PRESLEY?
SURE.WHAT'S IN IT?
PEANUT BUTTER, BANANAS,
BACON, AND COOL WHIP.
WHAT DOES THAT TASTE LIKE?
DEATH ON A PLATE.
YEAH, I'LL JUST GET
THE COFFEE.
I HEAR YOU HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
WHO'D YOU HEAR THAT FROM?
DOESN'T MATTER
WHO I HEARD IT FROM.
IS IT TRUE?
NO.
SO YOU DON'T
HAVE A BOYFRIEND
WHO'S LIVING
AND BREATHING
AND HAS NO IDEA
THAT YOU'RE A GRIM REAPER?
DID ROXY TELL YOU THAT?
TELL ME WHAT?
THAT I HAVE
A BOYFRIEND.
THAT HANDSOME DEVIL
I SAW YOU LEAVING WITH
LAST NIGHT?
IS THAT YOUR BOYFRIEND?NO.
OKAY.
HEY. HOW'D IT GO?
G-R-E-A-T.
IT WAS A SPELLING BEE.
SERIOUSLY, HOW'D IT GO?
F-A-N-T-A...
S-T-I-C.
HOW DO I GET IT
TO STOP?
WELL, GO ON, GEORGIE,
TELL HIM.
AS FAR AS SENSELESS,
BRUTAL DEATHS GO,
I'D SAY IT WENT BEAUTIFULLY.
YEAH, SO MAYBE
A SIMPLE THANK YOU
IS IN ORDER,
INSTEAD OF YOUR
CONSTANT IRRITATION, RUBIE.
MAYBE A LITTLE BIT
OF G-R-A-T...
UH...
...ITUDE.
FOR YOU AND YOU.
WHERE'S ROXY?
SHE HAS GOT A PERSONAL DAY.
WELL, WHY DON'T I HAVE
A PERSONAL DAY?
BECAUSE YOU'RE
AN F-U-C-K-U-P.
"FUCK UP" HAS TWO WORDS.
ACTUALLY,
"FUCK-UP" IS A HYPHENATE.
WELL, IT IS.
THIS IS IN
A BAD PART OF TOWN.
I KNOW THAT ADDRESS.
THAT'S THE LINKLATER
BOXING GYM.
SOUNDS SWEATY AND VIOLENT.
WHY DON'T YOU
KEEP HER COMPANY?
I THINK I'M PAST THE
"I NEED PROTECTION" STAGE,
DON'T YOU?
I DON'T THINK I'D CONSIDER
MASON'S COMPANY "PROTECTION."
WELL, WHATEVER IT IS,
NO THANKS.
YOU ALREADY HAVE
COMPANY TODAY, PRINCESS?
YOUR BOYFRIEND
RIDING SHOTGUN
FOR YOUR REAP?
I DON'T HAVE
A BOYFRIEND, OKAY?
A BOYFRIEND.
MASON, I WOULD LOVE IT
IF YOU COULD COME WITH ME
TO THE GYM.
I'D FEEL SAFER.
I WOULD BE SO HAPPY TO.
B-Y-E.
TELL ME ABOUT HER BOYFRIEND.
UH, KIFFANY?
I HAVEN'T MET HIM.
BLUEBERRY PANCAKES.
WHAT?
WHAT DID YOU DO?
I MADE BLUEBERRY PANCAKES.
YOU MAKE THOSE
WHEN YOU FEEL GUILTY.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
WHY ARE YOU DRESSED
LIKE A REALTOR?
BECAUSE I'M GOING OUT
JOB HUNTING.
WHY?
BECAUSE THEY GIVE YOU MONEY
AT THE END OF THE DAY.
I'M JUST LOOKING
FOR SOMETHING TEMPORARY.
YOU KNOW, OFFICE WORK.
SOUNDS BORING.
WELL, REGGIE,
IT'S EITHER THAT
OR WE SELL THE DOG
TO A CHINESE RESTAURANT.
THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
ALL RIGHT,
I GUESS THAT'S NOT
A GOOD IDEA.
GOLDEN RETRIEVERS
JUST AREN'T GOOD EATIN'.
SO WHEN YOU'RE AT WORK,
WHO'S GOING TO WATCH ME?
WHO DO YOU WANT TO WATCH YOU?
NO ONE.
DAISY HAS ALLEGED IN THE PAST
THAT SHE HAS HAD DALLIANCES
WITH MEN,
SEXUAL ESCAPADES
WITH PEOPLE WHO WERE ALIVE
WHILE SHE WAS A REAPER.
IF SO...
IT'S A BLUNDER.
CHARLIE CHAPLIN,
TYRONE POWERS, BABE RUTH...
I'VE HEARD THE STORIES.
DOUGLAS FAIRBANKS,
ERROL FLYNN,
WILLIAM HOLDEN--
I GET IT.
WILLIAM HOLDEN?YEAH, I DON'T KNOW
WHO THAT IS EITHER.
SUNSET BOULEVARD?
FACE DOWN IN
THE SWIMMING POOL?
JESUS.
THE POINT, GEORGE,
IS THAT, UH...
THESE ALLEGED
INDISCRETIONS...
THEY WERE NOT ON MY WATCH.
I AM NOT A SNITCH, RUBE.
I'M NOT TELLING ON DAISY.
GEORGIA,
SNITCHING IS NOT THE POINT.
THE POINT IS,
SHE SHOULDN'T BE INVOLVED
WITH SOMEONE LIVING.
THE POINT IS,
KEEP THE SYRUP
AWAY FROM THE EGGS.
I LIKE SYRUP ON MY EGGS.
WHO'S THAT?WHO'S WHO?
THIS.
GEORGE, RIGHT?
YEAH, DAISY TOLD ME
THIS IS
ONE OF HER HAUNTS.
HEY. RAY SUMMERS.
RUBE.
QUITE A DEATH GRIP
YOU GOT THERE, RUBE.
YOU SEEN MY GIRL?
OH, SHE JUST LEFT.
SO MUCH FOR TIMING.
WHAT'S YOUR STORY, RAY?
MY STORY IS THAT I'M
A TELEVISION PRODUCER.
YOU MAY HAVE SEEN MY PROGRAM.
IT'S--
I DON'T WATCH
THAT MUCH TELEVISION.
LET ME GUESS.
YOU'RE A READER.
I'M A READER.
HOW DO YOU KNOW DAISY, RAY?
MET HER IN A BAR,
BOUGHT HER A DRINK...
OR THREE.
WE MAY HAVE BEEN
A LITTLE OVER-SERVED
THAT NIGHT.
SO YOU'RE JUST
DRINKING BUDDIES?
NO. NO, NO.
DAISY'S MY, UH...
MY GOOD LUCK CHARM.
CHARM, PERHAPS.
GOOD LUCK...
NOT IN MY EXPERIENCE.
WELL, MAYBE NOT
IN YOUR EXPERIENCE, BUT...
ACTUALLY,
COME TO THINK OF IT,
THE NIGHT I MET HER,
SOME GUY DIED.
YOU WERE THERE.NO, I WASN'T.
I WASN'T.
SO HOW DO YOU
KNOW DAISY, RUBE?
THAT'S NOT ANY OF
YOUR BUSINESS.
WOW.
DON'T CANDY-COAT IT
FOR ME, RUBE.
IF I'M NOT WELCOME HERE--
YOU ARE NOT WELCOME HERE.
DID I SAY SOMETHING
TO OFFEND YOU?
NO.THEN WHAT'S
YOUR PROBLEM?
I JUST DON'T LIKE STRANGERS
ALL THAT MUCH,
AND I DID NOT INVITE YOU
TO SIT DOWN AT THIS TABLE
WITH PEOPLE YOU DO NOT KNOW.
ACTUALLY, RUBE,
I KNOW GEORGE HERE.
YOU DON'T KNOW ME.
OKAY.
YOU FOLKS HAVE A NICE DAY.
I DO NOT LIKE HIM.
DON'T YOU WANT
TO JUST SLAP THAT SMILE
RIGHT OFF HIS FACE?
YEAH, SO I REALLY
DON'T THINK
IT'S A GOOD IDEA
FOR YOU TO INVITE RAY
TO A REAP.
OH, SUDDENLY YOU'RE
THE RESPONSIBLE ONE.
COME ON.
IT'S RECKLESS.
HE MIGHT SEE SOMETHING.
PLEASE.
HE DOESN'T NOTICE
ANYTHING.
HE'S BLINDED BY LOVE.
HA!
YOU ARE FLIRTING
WITH DISASTER,
DAISY ADAIR.
YOU JUST DON'T LIKE IT
THAT I'M FLIRTING AT ALL.
COME ON.
I'M NOT INTERESTED IN YOU
IN THAT WAY ANYMORE...
ACTUALLY.
REALLY.
ANYMORE.
I BELIEVE YOU.GOOD.
I JUST DON'T WANT
TO SEE YOU GET HURT.
HOW'S IT GOING?
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
CRYSTAL.
UM, WILL MISS HERBIG
BE BACK SOON?
MM-HMM.
I DON'T LIKE HOSPITALS.
WHY?
WHO THE HELL
LIKES HOSPITALS?
WELL, LET'S SEE.
DOCTORS, NURSES,
ORDERLIES.
PEOPLE WHO ARE SICK
AND WANT TO GET BETTER.
PEOPLE WHO KNOW PEOPLE
WHO ARE SICK
AND WANT THEM TO GET BETTER.
I DON'T SEE ANYONE
AROUND HERE
WHO LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE
GETTING ANY BETTER.
WELL, IT'S THE
LONG-TERM CARE WARD.
THEY'RE PROBABLY
NOT GOING OUT
THE WAY THEY CAME IN.
DO WE KNOW HER?
WE DO.
NATURAL CAUSES
IS ONE OF THE...
NICER ASSIGNMENTS
FOR A REAPER,
ESPECIALLY IN A HOSPITAL.
NO CHASING ANYONE DOWN.
EVERYONE'S
GOT A NAME TAG.
NICE GIG.
EXCEPT EVERYONE'S
REALLY OLD.
YOU GOT SOMETHING
AGAINST OLD PEOPLE?
THEY JUST FREAK ME OUT
A LITTLE,
AND THE REALLY OLD ONES
IRRITATE ME.
THAT'S NICE.
YOU KNOW WHEN THEY'RE
CROSSING A STREET
AT THE "WALK" SIGN,
AND THE TIME
IS TICKING BY,
AND EVEN IF THEY START
RIGHT AWAY,
THEY STILL NEVER
MAKE IT ACROSS
ON TIME.
THAT IRRITATES YOU?
THEY'RE REALLY SLOW.
GO FIND YOUR REAP.
OKAY.
HOW?
HEY, BUD,
DO YOU HAVE AN N. ROMMEY
ON THIS FLOOR?
IT'S N. ROMMEY,
LIKE "MOMMY."
NINA. ROOM 331.
SEE? IT'S A NICE GIG.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
♪ MY BONNY LIES
OVER THE OCEAN ♪
OVER THE SEA ♪
♪ MY BONNY LIES
OVER-- ♪
ARE WE THERE YET?
WHERE?ARE WE THERE YET?
WELL, I DON'T
BELIEVE WE ARE.
ARE YOU N. ROMMEY?
YES. NO.
♪ MY BONNY LIES
OVER THE OCEAN ♪
OVER THE SEA ♪
♪ MY BONNY LIES
OVER THE OCEAN ♪
SO BRING BACK
MY BONNY TO ME.
[ LAUGHS ]
LIKE I SAID,
THEY FREAK ME OUT A LITTLE.
NOW, YOU KNOW IT'S BETTER
WHEN YOU STAY IN YOUR ROOM.
MY ROOM.
UH, IS THIS...
NINA?
I AM MRS. NINA ROMMEY.
HOW DO YOU DO?
NINA, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
WE'RE HEARING
A STORY TODAY.
IT'S A FAIRY TALE.
WELL, ONCE UPON A TIME,
YOU WERE ALIVE,
THEN YOU DIED.
THE END.
OH, HEY, I KNOW YOU.
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO WAS KILLED
BY A TOILET SEAT.
GOD, WILL ANYONE
EVER LET THAT GO?
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH, BLAH--
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
I'M PENNY.
I'M GEORGE.
NINA, THIS IS GEORGE.
SHE'S COME TO
TAKE CARE OF YOU.
WE HAVE TO GO.
WE REALLY DON'T
WANT TO BE LATE.
OH, WE WON'T BE.
KATE HEPBURN BOXED.
ALSO KITTY LOMBARD.
IT'S A GREAT
ACTING EXERCISE.
I NEED TO FIND MY REAP
BEFORE RAY GETS HERE.
GOOD IDEA.
HE'LL BE DEAD AND GONE
BEFORE RAY EVEN SHOWS UP.
BOXERS ARE
REALLY BEAUTIFUL.
RAY'S REALLY BEAUTIFUL.
I'LL TELL YOU WHO'S
BEAUTIFUL, DAISY.
I'LL TELL YOU
WHO'S BEAUTIFUL.
IT'S FUCKING ME.
I'M BEAUTIFUL. YEAH.
YEAH, I'M HOT.
I'M HOT. I CAN BOX.
I CAN BOX.
WHO IS IT, CROWD? WHO IS IT?
IT'S KID MASON!
YEAH!
KID MASON. KID MASON.
YEAH, THE MASONATOR.
THE MASONATOR.
SHAKE IT OUT, SHAKE IT OUT,
SHAKE IT OUT.
YEAH, YOU'RE NOT SO
FUCKING BEAUTIFUL NOW,
ARE YOU, RAY?
WHOA! EASY, TIGER.
OOH. SORRY, MATE.
DAISY CALLED ME.GOOD FOR YOU.
ASKED ME TO
MEET HER HERE.
AND?
AND I'M HERE.ARE YOU HER LAP DOG, RAY?
[ BARKS ]
DID YOU JUST
BARK AT ME?
NO. NO.
CAN YOU BOX, RAY?
CAN YOU?
BIT OF BOXING, HEY?
CAN YOU? HUH?
I'VE HAD MY SHARE OF FIGHTS,
IF THAT'S YOUR QUESTION.
REALLY?
OH, I'M JUST ASKING,
BECAUSE, UH, YOU KNOW...
NOT EVERY MAN CAN BOX.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
SOMETHING YOU WANT TO
SAY TO ME, MASON?
NO.
WELL, THEN...
DON'T STAND
SO FUCKING CLOSE.
SERIOUSLY.
STEP BACK.
YOU STEP BACK.
OKAY.
OKAY, MASON, YOU WIN.
YOU GET TO TAKE HOME
THE BIG PRIZE.
OH, NO, WAIT.
I DO.
FUCK OFF, YOU RIGHTEOUS
FUCKING COCKSUCKER.
PARDON ME,
I'M LOOKING FOR A...
I THINK IT'S
A MR. WASHINGTON.
IT'S KID.
KID WASHINGTON.
YOU ARE JUST SO MUCH
MORE HANDSOME UP CLOSE
THAN IN THE RING.
I'M NOT THE KID.
OH. OH.
WHAT CAN I DO
FOR YOU, MISS?
OH, I...
I JUST WANTED TO MEET YOU.
I'M KID WASHINGTON,
AND YOU ARE...
I'M DAISY. DAISY ADAIR.
MM-HMM.
MY FATHER
USED TO TALK ABOUT YOU.
OH, IS THAT SO?
YEAH, HE SAID
YOUR HARRISON FIGHT WAS...
A CLASSIC.
15 ROUNDS.
YEAH, THAT WAS
SOME FIGHT.
WELL, IT'S AN HONOR
TO MEET YOU, KID.
WELL, NICE OF YOU
TO STOP BY TODAY, MISS.
ALL RIGHT, LOUIS.
SHOWING OFF
IS AN EASY WAY
TO GET HURT.
[ BUZZING ]
CHRIS, CODE BLUE
IN 301.
GET ME DR. ROTHSCHILD.
IS THAT THE SCHOOL BELL?
SURE.WE'RE GOING TO BE
LATE FOR CLASS.
OH, NO, WE WON'T.
WE'LL BE RIGHT ON TIME.
OOH. THANK YOU.
OH, I HAVE
TO TAKE THESE.
I'D SEEN A LOT
OF PEOPLE DIE--
HIT BY A BUS,
MAULED BY A BEAR,
TORN UP BY A LAWNMOWER--
BUT THIS QUIET MISTAKE
I COULDN'T MAKE SENSE OF.
THEN AGAIN,
NEITHER COULD NINA.
I KNOW I WASN'T SUPPOSED
TO INTERFERE,
BUT I JUST WANTED TO STOP HER
BEFORE IT WAS TOO LATE.
NINA.
LET'S GO BACK
TO YOUR ROOM.
YOUR HAIR IS SO PRETTY.
THANK YOU.
GET ME OUT OF THIS.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
TWO BOYS FIGHTING OVER ME?
IT'S MY DREAM.
LOVELY.
I'M NOT FIGHTING OVER YOU,
BUT THIS COULD HURT.
YOU HEAL FAST.
THAT DOESN'T TAKE AWAY
FROM THE HURTY-PAINY BIT.
YOU FORGOT TO KISS ME
FOR GOOD LUCK.
NOT IN FRONT OF MASON.
HEY, GO EASY ON HIM.
EASY ON HIM?
I THINK THAT SHIP'S
PRETTY MUCH SAILED.
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO
BE LIKE THAT?
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO BE MEAN?
HEY, I'M JUST FINISHING
WHAT YOU STARTED,
SWEETHEART.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO PUT
THE GUY IN HARM'S WAY.
NO, I DIDN'T.
YOU'RE INVOLVED
WITH TWO MEN, DAISY.
THAT STORY
NEVER ENDS WELL.
NOW, SHUT UP AND KISS ME.
[ BELL DINGS ]
LET'S GO.
WE ALL LIKE WORKING
WITH RICKY.
THAT'S NICE.
RICKY WAS DOING
VELUM BINDING ON, LIKE,
HIS THIRD DAY HERE.
DELORES DIDN'T EVEN
TALK TO ME ABOUT THAT
KIND OF RESPONSIBILITY
UNTIL AT LEAST WEEK TWO.
AND HE'S EXCELLENT
ABOUT RECYCLING.
I'M SORRY,
I DON'T KNOW WHO
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
AREN'T YOU RICKY'S MOM?
NO.
HE SAID HIS MOM
WAS VISITING HIM TODAY
AT LUNCH.
YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU COULD BE HIS MOM.
WELL, I'M NOT HER.ARE YOU SURE?
YEAH, I'M HERE
TO BE PLACED...
FOR A JOB.
THAT'S...
THAT'S REALLY BRAVE.
"BRAVE?"
YEAH, I MEAN, TO JUST...
DO YOU WANT
HALF A SANDWICH?
IT'S TUNA.
NO, THANKS.
HI. I'M DELORES HERBIG.
CRYSTAL TELLS ME YOU'RE...
JOY. JOY LASS.
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU FOLLOW ME
TO MY CUBICLE,
AND WE'LL HAVE A CHAT,
MS. LASS...
OR IS IT MRS.?
MS. IS FINE.
COMING?
YES.
I'M A LITTLE RUSTY,
SO HELP ME OUT HERE.
IS THAT THE TWO-STEP
OR THE CHA-CHA?
CHA, CHA-CHA-CHANCE
TO BEAT YOUR WHITE,
PASTY ASS, MOTHERFUCKER.
I'M NOT FAMILIAR
WITH THAT ONE.
NEED A LITTLE HELP THERE,
GINGER?
SHOULD I JUST KILL HIM
OR SEND HIM TO THE HOSPITAL?
SERIOUSLY,
DON'T HURT HIM.
PLAY NICE.
IT'S A FIGHT, DAISY.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
PICK A CORNER.
I DON'T WANT TO
HE LOOKS LIKE A BLEEDER.
THE DRUNKS BLEED LIKE HELL.
YEAH, I DON'T NEED
TO SEE THIS.
I DON'T NEED TO SEE
ANY OF THIS.
HEY. HEY!
DON'T WALK AWAY FROM ME
WHEN I'M TALKING TO YOU.
COME ON, BITCH.
NOW YOU'VE MADE ME MAD.
I'M ACTUALLY
REALLY SORRY, RAY,
BECAUSE THIS IS
A GENTLEMAN'S SPORT,
ISN'T IT, SO...
SO FUCK OFF,
BITCHETY-BITCHY-BITCH!
COME ON!
YEAH, GO ON, DARLING.
HIDE THAT PRETTY FACE
OF YOURS, SWEETHEART,
BECAUSE YOU ARE
GOING TO
LEAVE HERE HURTING.
YOUR UNBORN CHILDREN
AND GRANDCHILDREN
AND STEP-HALF...
BLOODY TWO-HEADED NEPHEWS
ARE GOING TO BE FEELING
THE FUCKING PAIN,
BEEOTCH! COME ON!
LIKE THE PAIN YOU FEEL
EVERY TIME I TAKE
YOUR PRECIOUS DAISY HOME
AND FUCK HER?
WHOA. KID.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
GET UP, KID. COME ON.
AM I GETTING UP?
NO.
OH.YEAH.
SORRY.
YOU'RE DOWN
FOR THE COUNT.
NIGHT-NIGHT.
I'M SLEEPY.
I KNOW.
WE SHOULDN'T CUT CLASS TODAY.
COME ON, UNDER THE COVERS.
BOOK REPORTS ARE DUE TODAY.
DID YOU READ THE BOOK?
I LOVED IT.
YEAH, ME TOO.
ARE WE THERE YET?
I THINK SO.
I LOVE THE EIGHTH GRADE.
YEAH.
EIGHTH GRADE WAS FUN.
HISTORY MAJOR,
WITH A BUSINESS MINOR
IN COLLEGE,
EXECUTIVE SECRETARY
FOR TWO LAW FIRMS...
AND I KNOW GREGG SHORTHAND
AND MEDICAL SHORTHAND.
OH, WONDERFUL.
YOUR RESUME
IS SO WELL-ORGANIZED.
LET'S JUST INPUT YOU
INTO THE DATABANK.
I KNOW I'VE HEARD
YOUR NAME BEFORE.
YOU KNOW, YOUR NAME
SOUNDS FAMILIAR TO ME
AS WELL.
REALLY? HUH.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
ARE YOU ANY RELATION
TO THE YOUNG WOMAN
WHO DIED?
THAT WAS MY DAUGHTER.
GEORGE.
I HIRED HER.
GEORGIA LASS.
YOU'RE THE WOMAN
WHO GAVE HER THE JOB.
YOU CALLED THE HOUSE.
YOU AND I SPOKE
ON THE PHONE.
I'M SORRY FOR YOUR LOSS.
THANK YOU.
I DIDN'T SPEND MUCH TIME
WITH YOUR DAUGHTER.
SHE SEEMED SWEET.
DID SHE?NO.
SHE SEEMED COMPLICATED.
SMART.
WHAT ELSE?
DIFFICULT.
A HANDFUL...
BUT PROMISING,
WHICH IS WHY I HIRED HER.
WE DON'T HAVE TO
DO THIS NOW, MS. LASS.
WE CAN RESCHEDULE,
OR NOT DO IT AT ALL--
NO.
I'M HERE.
I'M FINE.
I WANT TO WORK.
IT'S "JOY."
OKAY.
WHAT DO YOU WANT
TO DO, JOY?
WHAT'S YOUR PASSION?
WHAT DO YOU LIKE?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, UH,
WE HAVE A NUMBER OF, UM...
I LIKE
MAKING LISTS.
I LIKE BOXES.
FILES.
SHELVES.
SELF-STICKING LABELS.
ME TOO.
SO SHE WAS IN THIS OFFICE?
YES.
WHAT DID GEORGE DO
THAT LAST DAY, FOR WORK?
I REALLY, UH...
DON'T REMEMBER.
OKAY, EVERYONE,
I KNOW THAT YOU ALL THINK
THAT YOU COULDN'T LIVE
WITHOUT THE INTERNET,
BUT BEFORE ONLINE RESEARCH,
THERE WERE CARD CATALOGUES
AND PAPER CARDS
IN LIBRARY BOOK POCKETS.
OH, REGGIE, DON'T PLAY
WITH THOSE BOOKS.
THEY HAVEN'T BEEN
BAR-CODED YET.
THEY STILL HAVE THOSE
ANTIQUATED CHECK-OUT
CARDS IN THEM.
SY BENJAMIN,
IF THAT IS A SKIN MAGAZINE
I SEE YOU HOLDING,
SO HELP ME...
DO YOU KNOW WHO THIS IS?
I DON'T REMEMBER.
THIS IS YOUR HUSBAND,
WILLIAM.
WHO?
THERE WILL BE A QUIZ
ON THIS MATERIAL.
YEAH, I KNOW,
AND ACTUALLY,
I THINK YOU'RE LATE
FOR THAT QUIZ,
SO THIS WAY...
NO.
OH!
NINA, YOU REALLY NEED
TO FOLLOW ME.
DON'T TELL ME WHAT TO DO.
YOU'RE DEAD, NINA.
THIS IS THE LADY
WHO BRUSHES MY HAIR.
YES. THAT IS
YOUR DAUGHTER, BETH...
AND YOU ARE DEAD.
SO WHO IS THIS,
THIS ROSIE?
NOBODY YOU KNOW.
IS IT SOMEBODY
YOU KNEW?
IS SHE RELATED TO YOU?
YES.
BEAU CHENE.
THAT'S A DECENT HOSPITAL?
THEY TAKE GOOD CARE
OF PEOPLE THERE?
NO, RUBE,
THEY WATER THEM ONCE A WEEK.
LOOK AT YOU,
DRIVING ON THE WRONG SIDE
OF THE ROAD.
IT'S NOT GOOD.
THANKS FOR THIS.
HOW'S DER WAFFLE HAUS?GOOD.
KIFFANY?FINE.
YOUR MERRY BAND
OF REAPERS?THEY'RE AWFUL.
OKAY, YOU HAVE
TO HELP ME.
SHE'S ONE OF
THE BETTER ONES.
BETTER ONE WHAT?
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM, GEORGE?
I CAN'T GET HER TO GO.
SHE WON'T FOLLOW ME.
NINA FORGETS THINGS.
YEAH, I PICKED UP
ON THAT.
WHAT PENNY'S SAYING
IS SHE HAS NO IDEA
SHE'S DEAD.
I GET THAT.
HOW DO I GET HER
TO GO?
I'M TELLING YOU, GEORGE,
YOU HAVE TO GET NINA
TO CONNECT TO HER OWN DEATH
BEFORE SHE CAN MOVE ON.
HOW THE FUCK AM I
SUPPOSED TO DO THAT?
OOH, SHE'S GOT
A MOUTH ON HER.
ALWAYS A PLEASURE, PENNY.
I'LL SEE YOU AROUND
THE CAMPUS.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
YOU'RE JUST BOLTING?
I GOT FISH TO FRY,
LITTLE GEORGIA.
HEY, I'M ON MY LUNCH BREAK.
OH, COME ON. PLEASE?
SORRY, HONEY, CAN'T DO IT.
COME ON. I DON'T...
I DON'T REALLY LIKE
OLD PEOPLE.
THEN YOU'RE ONE LUCKY GIRL.
HOW SO?BECAUSE YOU'LL
NEVER BE ONE.
LISTEN, I HAVE TO REPORT
NINA'S TIME OF DEATH
TO THE HOSPITAL,
BUT I'LL DELAY
AS LONG AS I CAN.
SO...SO?
BETTER GET A MOVE ON...
PEANUT.
I WOULD NEVER BECOME OLD.
DEAD AND YOUNG
HAS TO BE BETTER THAN
ALIVE AND OLD.
ISN'T IT? RIGHT?
AT LEAST I REMEMBER THINGS.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
YOU'RE LABELING.
I LIKE TO LABEL.
WHEN SOMETHING BAD HAPPENS.
I'M JUST REWORKING
OUR SHELVING SYSTEM.
ONCE I STARTED DOING THAT,
I REALIZED IT WAS TIME
TO REORGANIZE THE PANTRY.
[ DOORBELL CHIMES ]OH, HONEY,
COULD YOU GET THAT?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M NOT GOING TO KEEP BUYING
THESE CHEWY GRANOLA
BAR THINGIES ANYMORE
IF YOU DON'T EAT THEM.
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE I'M NOT
MADE OF MONEY HERE.
HI, BOY.
HI, CLAIRE.
OH, I'M SORRY
TO BOTHER YOU,
BUT YOUR DOG...
YOUR DOG
DROPPED A ZOOMER
INTO MY NASTURTIUMS.
OH.
WELL, CLAIRE,
AREN'T ZOOMERS
SUPPOSED TO BE GOOD
FOR NASTURTIUMS?
SMALL FLOWERS,
BIG DOG.
THESE FLOWERS WON A PRIZE
AT THE PICKWICK CLUB
LAST YEAR.
YEAH, I REMEMBER.
SO IF YOU COULD JUST BE
A LITTLE MORE CAREFUL
WITH YOUR DOG...
UH, YEAH, WE WILL.
WON'T WE?
DON'T LOOK AT ME.
I WASN'T HOME.
QUITE A PROJECT
YOU'VE GOT GOING ON HERE.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
ARE YOU MOVING?
NO, NO, I'M JUST, UH...
REORGANIZING MY KITCHEN.
OH, IT'S BREATHTAKING.
THANK YOU.
YOU CAN SEE WHERE
EVERYTHING IS RIGHT AWAY.
WELL, A PLACE FOR EVERYTHING,
AND EVERYTHING IN ITS PLACE.
DID YOU DO ALL THIS
YOURSELF?
I DID.
DO YOU THINK...
WOULD YOU EVER COME OVER
AND DO THIS TO MY KITCHEN?
YEAH, I COULD DO THAT...
FOR 75 AN HOUR.
HOW ABOUT THURSDAY?
THURSDAY'S GOOD.
WHAT DID RUBE SAY?
HE SAID I HAVE TO MAKE HER
CONNECT TO HER OWN DEATH.
THIS BLOODY JOB
NEVER BLOODY ENDS,
DOES IT?
♪ K-K-K-KATY
♪ BEAUTIFUL KATY
♪ YOU'RE THE ONLY G-G-GIRL
♪ THAT I ADORE
WHAT'S WITH
THE POST-ITS?
SHE FORGETS THINGS.
THEY REMIND HER
OF THINGS...
OR NOT.
MASON, DON'T.
IT'S NOT HELPING.
YOU'RE GOING TO
GET HER ALL RILED UP.
YEAH, FIGHT'S OVER, MASON.WHAT FIGHT?
RAY HIT HIM.I HIT HIM BACK,
AND HE NEARLY
BLOODY DIED.
♪ WHEN THE M-M-MOON SHINES
OVER THE COWSHED ♪
YOU KNOW WHAT, DAISY?
RAY'S AN ASSHOLE.RAY'S AN ASSHOLE.
SEE? NINA CAN'T
REMEMBER A THING,
AND EVEN SHE CAN
FIGURE THAT ONE OUT.
YEAH, WELL,
I'M NOT GOING TO
SEE HIM ANYMORE.
REALLY?I'M DONE.
GOOD. EXCELLENT.
MOVING ON--
♪ I'LL BE WAITING
AT THE K-K-KITCHEN DOOR ♪
SO, THIS IS NINA?
THIS IS NINA,
WHETHER SHE KNOWS IT
OR NOT.
HELLO, NINA.
HELLO, MY DARLING.
HELLO.
I HAVE TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING.
YOU HAVE TO LISTEN TO ME
VERY CAREFULLY.
IT MIGHT UPSET YOU,
BUT LISTEN TO ME, OKAY?
JAMES BOND.
YOU'RE DEAD.
YOU SNUFFED IT.
SHAKEN BUT NOT STIRRED.
OKAY, SHE'S BATTY.
SHE'S GONE. SHE'S GONE.
IS THERE ANYTHING
VALUABLE IN HERE?
NO. SHE CAN'T
REMEMBER A THING.
SHE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW
WHO SHE IS.
I HAVE A THOUGHT.
YOU'RE VERY PRETTY.
OH, THANK YOU.
PERFECT.
SHE SEEMS
PRETTY LUCID TO ME.
[ KNOCKS ]
DAD?
HELLO, BETH.
YOUR HUSBAND, WILLIAM.
YOUR DAUGHTER, BETH.
DAD, I HAVE
SOME HORRIBLE NEWS.
WHAT IS IT?
MOM IS DEAD.
DEAD? YOUR MOTHER?
DEAD? NINA?
SITTING RIGHT THERE?
DEAD?
WOE IS US.
WOE IS ME.
JUST WOE.
DEAD.
REALLY FUCKING DEAD.
WAS I ALL RIGHT?
WAS THAT GOOD?YEAH, IT WAS INCREDIBLE.
I HAD FUN.YEAH, BUT NOT THAT GREAT.
HOW DO YOU EXPLAIN
TO SOMEONE WHAT DEATH IS?
WHAT DO I SAY?
"DEATH IS LIKE..."
WHAT?
IT'S LIKE A PLAY, RIGHT?
THE SWAN SONG,
THE LAST ACT...
[ COCKS GUN ]
THE FAT LADY SINGING.
THAT'S WHAT IT IS.
THE FINAL CURTAIN.
HOW DO I TELL SOMEONE
WHO DOESN'T UNDERSTAND
THAT THE SHOW'S OVER?
HOW DO I TELL SOMEONE
WHO DOESN'T QUITE
UNDERSTAND THE WORDS
THAT IT'S OKAY TO LEAVE?
REGGIE, LOOK AT THAT FACE.
LOOK AT THE MONKEY FACE.
YES, YOU ARE.
YOU ARE SO CUTE.
DOES THE
LITTLE MONKEY KNOW
HOW PRECIOUS SHE IS?
SHE IS SO PERFECT.
JUST PERFECT.
DADDY LOVES YOU.
MOM?YEAH, GEORGE?
I DON'T WANT
REGGIE TO DIE.
OKAY.
THAT'S GOOD, SWEETIE.
WELL, NO ONE HERE WANTS
ANYONE TO DIE, GEORGE.
WHAT DO WE DO?
NOT A THING.
IT'S SIBLING RIVALRY.
SPOCK SAYS IT'S
COMPLETELY NORMAL.
"I DON'T WANT
REGGIE TO DIE"
IS NOT NORMAL.
RELAX, JOY.
IT'LL DISAPPEAR.
SHE'LL FORGET
SHE EVER SAID IT.
HOW'S YOUR BOOK,
SWEETIE?
PRETTY GOOD.
HOW'S YOUR THUMB?
HEY, COULD I HAVE ONE?DID YOU SEE SHE MADE
A RAISIN SANDWICH?
PUT A RAISIN
RIGHT IN THERE.
LOOK WHAT SHE DID.
SHE DID THAT HERSELF.
LOOK,
SHE MADE THAT.
SHE DID THAT?
NINA COULDN'T MOVE ON
BECAUSE SHE COULDN'T
REMEMBER,
BUT MOST OF US ARE HAUNTED
BY THE THINGS WE CAN'T FORGET.
ARE WE THERE YET?ARE WE THERE YET?
ARE WE THERE YET?STOP IT!
GREAT, NOW SHE WON.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO?
SHE'S FORGOTTEN
EVERYTHING.
I CAN'T TALK TO HER
ABOUT HER MEMORIES
BECAUSE I DON'T
KNOW HER.
IT'S LIKE
SHE'S NOT EVEN HERE.
IT'S A JOKE.
IT'S LIKE THERE'S NO
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
BEING DEAD AND ALIVE.
I NEED A DRINK.
YEAH, I CAN'T LET HIM
DRINK ALONE.
WELL, DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
WHAT?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
THE POST-IT?
BETH.
MY DAUGHTER, BETH.
DO YOU WANT TO
HEAR A STORY, NINA?
OH, I LOVE STORIES.
WELL, ONCE,
THERE WAS A GIRL
NAMED GEORGE.
SHE WAS 18 YEARS OLD,
AND SHE DIDN'T HAVE
A HUSBAND WILLIAM,
SHE DIDN'T HAVE
A DAUGHTER NAMED BETH,
BUT SHE HAD A MOM,
A FATHER, AND A SISTER,
AND ONE DAY,
SHE WENT OUTSIDE.
IT WAS A SUNNY DAY,
FEW CLOUDS,
BUT AN ORDINARY DAY.
AND SHE WENT OUT
TO GET SOME LUNCH,
AND THIS MAN...
HE STOPPED ME,
AND HE TALKED TO ME,
AND HE KNEW MY LAST NAME.
I TOLD HIM TO LEAVE ME ALONE,
BUT THEN SOMETHING
FROM THE SKY FELL,
AND I DIDN'T FEEL ANYTHING.
I COULDN'T REMEMBER ANYTHING,
AT FIRST,
BUT THEN I DID.
I REALIZED...
I DIED.
I...
DIED.
I'M DEAD.
THAT'S RIGHT.
YES. THAT'S RIGHT.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME, NINA.
I DIDN'T KNOW NINA'S STORY.
I COULD ONLY TELL HER MINE.
IT WAS THE ONLY STORY
I REALLY KNEW.
[SOFT WHOOSHING]
I GUESS DEATH
MAKES EVERYTHING GROW COLD.
I HADN'T BEEN THINKING
ABOUT REGGIE AT ALL LATELY,
OR MY MOM, OR MY DAD.
I HADN'T BEEN THINKING
ABOUT THEM AT ALL,
AND I BET THEY WEREN'T
THINKING ABOUT ME.
EITHER WAY,
MY AFTERLIFE WAS A SECRET.
[ CROAKING ]
ANYTHING ELSE
WAS JUST TOO DANGEROUS.
♪ MY BONNY LIES
OVER THE OCEAN ♪
OVER THE SEA ♪
♪ MY BONNY LIES
OVER THE OCEAN... ♪
♪ SO BRING BACK
MY BONNY ♪
♪ TO ME
WE WERE JUST GETTING
HOME FROM THE HOSPITAL.
I DIDN'T ASK YOU
WHERE YOU WERE.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE, RAY?
WAITING FOR YOU.
WELL, NOT YOU,
NOT YOU, BUT YOU.
YOU LEFT THE GYM
WITHOUT SAYING GOODBYE.
I'M SORRY.
GOODBYE.
I THINK
YOU SHOULD PISS OFF.
I THINK YOU SHOULD
STAY OUT OF THIS, GINGER.
SOMEBODY DIE
AT THE HOSPITAL?
NO.SOMEBODY DIED AT
THE GYM TODAY,
BUT THEN, YOU KNEW THAT,
AND THE NIGHT WE MET,
AND TWO DAYS AGO.
I'M BEGINNING TO THINK
THAT YOU'RE BAD LUCK.
YEAH. I AM.
YEAH.
THAT'S WHAT YOUR FRIEND RUBE
TOLD ME THIS MORNING.
YOU MET RUBE?
MM-HMM.
HE WASN'T VERY NICE TO ME.
THEN AGAIN,
NONE OF YOU
HAS BEEN VERY NICE TO ME.
YOU REALLY SHOULD
LEAVE NOW.
OKAY.
I'LL GO.
AND DON'T COME BACK.
I'M DONE WITH YOU.
GOOD FOR YOU.
I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT
TO END IT.
JUST ONE THING,
SWEETIE.
YOU DON'T END THINGS.
I END THEM.
YOU DON'T TELL ME
YOU'RE DONE. I DO.
YOU'RE WORSE
THAN BAD LUCK.
YOU'RE
A BLACK FUCKING HOLE.
FUCK YOU.
YOU'RE NOT AS GENTEEL
AS YOU LOOK, DAISY.
IN FACT,
AS PRETTY AS YOU ARE,
I JUST CAN'T
SHAKE THE FEELING
THAT YOU'RE REALLY
JUST A CHEAP HILLBILLY
PIECE OF TAIL.
HE'S DEAD.
HE'S DEAD?
I... I...
I'M SORRY.I'M NOT.
THERE'S...
THERE'S NO POST-IT.
AND THERE'S NO
FUCKING SOUL.
FUCKING...
IS THERE A SHOVEL
IN HERE?
THERE'S GOT TO BE
A SHOVEL, HASN'T THERE?
IS THERE?
[ WHOOSHING ]
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
THIS IS ALL
MY FUCKING FAULT.
IT'S MY FAULT.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT,
AND YOU'RE IN IT NOW.
YOU'RE IN IT NOW.
YOU ARE IN IT NOW.STOP IT.
IT'S NOBODY'S FAULT.
UH, AND IT'S DONE.
ALL RIGHT?YEAH.
WE KEEP THIS
TO OURSELVES,
AND NO ONE
NEEDS TO KNOW.
WHAT THE FUCK
WAS THAT?
HOW THE FUCK
DID YOU KNOW
THAT WAS GOING TO HAPPEN,
THAT GRAVELING?
BECAUSE I'VE
SEEN IT BEFORE,
AND HE WAS RIGHT.
I'M BAD LUCK.
THERE ARE THINGS INSIDE YOU
THAT NO ONE WANTS TO FACE,
THINGS THAT YOU KEEP SECRET,
EVEN FROM YOURSELF...
BUT SECRETS ARE FUNNY.
THE THINGS THAT
YOU TRY TO HIDE
ALWAYS TURN OUT TO BE
THE THINGS YOU CAN'T FORGET.