[♪♪]
[GEORGE]:  ONCE UPON A TIME,
THERE WAS TRAVELER
ON HORSEBACK
WHO FINDS HIMSELF
FACING A SWAMP,
AND HE DOESN'T KNOW
WHETHER TO GO AROUND
OR TRY TO WADE THROUGH.
THE TRAVELER
ASKS A LOCAL BOY,
"TELL ME, LOCAL BOY,
DOES THE SWAMP
HAVE A HARD BOTTOM?"
AND THE BOY TELLS HIM
THAT IT DOES.
SO THE TRAVELER
GUIDES HIS HORSE
INTO THE SWAMP,
AND THEY BEGIN TO SINK
DEEPER AND DEEPER
INTO THE MUCK.
HE SHOUTS TO THE BOY,
"I THOUGHT YOU SAID
IT HAS A HARD BOTTOM."
AND THE BOY SAYS
"IT DOES, MR. TRAVELER.
YOU'RE JUST NOT THERE YET."
TODAY?
TODAY. THAT'S WHY
I PROMOTED YOU.
[GEORGE]:
AND THE SINKING BEGINS.
I NOTICED THAT
YOU HAVEN'T SIGNED UP
FOR THE ANNUAL
HAPPY TIME RETREAT.
RIGHT.
THE SIGN-UP SHEET
IS FIRMLY TAPED
TO THE MICROWAVE, MILLIE.
HAVE YOU NOT SEEN IT?
I SAW THE SHEET,
IT'S JUST THAT...
OH, OH!OH!
[GEORGE]:  A NIGHT IN THE WOODS
WITH THESE FREAKS
SCARES ME MORE
THAN BEING DEAD.
WE ONLY RETREAT ONCE A YEAR.
THAT'S WHAT MAKES IT ANNUAL.
WHY RETREAT AT ALL?
WHO'S ATTACKING US?
ALWAYS THE CUTE JOKE.
THAT'S YOUR DEFENSE MECHANISM.
WHAT?SARCASM.
THAT'S HOW YOU KEEP PEOPLE
AT A SAFE DISTANCE.
[GEORGE]:  NO, I DON'T.
YOU DO.
YOU USE HUMOR.
FOR OTHERS,
IT'S AGGRESSIVE BODY PIERCINGS
AND FACIAL TATTOOS...
THANKS, SKEETER.
I'M NOT TRYING
TO DISTANCE ANYBODY.
I MEAN,
LOOK AT YOUR CUBICLE.
IT'S AS BARE
AS A POP STAR'S MIDRIFF.
I ENJOY
A CLUTTER-FREE WORK SPACE.
NOT A SINGLE PHOTO
OF A FRIEND OR FAMILY.
OH, MAKES ME SAD.
HEY, GUYS.
JUICE BARN RUN.
OH, TODD, COUNT ME IN.
I CAN'T RISK ANOTHER
LOW-BLOOD-SUGAR EPISODE TODAY.
YOU IN, MILLIE?
MILLIE, MILLIE, MILLIE.
WOULD IT KILL YOU
TO BE PART OF THE TEAM?
IT'S JUST, I'VE GOT
SO MUCH WORK TO DO, DELORES,
AND IT'S A HALF-DAY
FOR ME, SO--
WELL, HALF-DAYS ARE ONE THING,
BUT HALF-ASSED COMMITMENT
TO YOUR CO-WORKERS
IS QUITE ANOTHER.
NOW, IF I DON'T GO GET
THAT RASPBERRY RAZZMATAZZ,
I CAN'T BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR MY ACTIONS.
REALLY.
LEGALLY.
[GEORGE]:  HOW COULD
I TELL DELORES
THAT IT WAS HARD
TO PLAY FOR HER TEAM
WHEN I HAD ALREADY
BEEN DRAFTED BY
THE OTHER SIDE?
AND WITH A NEW MEMBERSHIP,
WE OFFER TWO PERSONAL
TRAINING SESSIONS.
CAN WE TAKE THEM
WITH THIS ONE?
WITH DIEGO?
OF COURSE.
I WONDER IF HE MAKES
HOUSE CALLS.
USE YOUR  ESPANOL.
NUESTROS NOMBRES SON
CHLOE Y ZOE.
MI CASA
ES SU CASA, DIEGO.
LADIES,
I AM BRAZILIAN.
I SPEAK PORTUGUESE.
THAT DOESN'T MAKE
ANY SENSE, BUT OKAY.
PARDON ME.
EXCUSE ME.
SAY SOMETHING
IN PORTUGUESE FOR ME.
DID YOU GO TO THE GYM
WHEN YOU WERE ALIVE?
I DIED IN 1938.
FOR EXERCISE,
WE DRANK SLOE GIN
AND SMOKED LUCKY STRIKES.
HI. WOULD YOU LIKE TO TRY
A REV-N UP BAR?
IT'S FREE.
15 GRAMS OF PROTEIN
AND LOADS OF FIBER.
NO THANKS.
HEY, WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF THESE GUYS?
FOR WHAT?MILLIE'S FAMILY.
WELL, THEY'RE VERY
ATTRACTIVE, AND THEY
LOOK REPUBLICAN.
YOU THINK?
YEAH. ISN'T THAT
WHAT YOU ARE?NO.
I NEVER VOTED,
BUT I'M NOT THAT.
WHAT WERE YOU?I WAS AN ACTRESS.
WELL, I LIKE
THE WAY THEY LOOK.
CONFIDENT,
LIKE WINNERS.
WHAT KIND OF RACQUETS
ARE THEY HOLDING?
[GRAVELING GROWLING]
SQUASH.
[CRASH]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
HE DROPPED THE BARBELL.
OH, NICE GOING, ZOE.
I SEE YOU JUST HAD
TO ADD AN EXTRA PIN
TO YOUR MAP,
DIDN'T YOU?
YOU JUST HAD TO HAVE
ONE MORE COUNTRY.
OH, REALLY?
AND THAT'S NOT
WHY YOU NAILED
THAT MOHAMMED GUY
LAST WEEK?
CAN WE CHANGE
INTO SOMETHING TAILORED?
I'M AFRAID IT'S
CASUAL DEATH DAY.
WILL YOU TELL ME
WHEN I DO THAT?
USE HUMOR
TO DISTANCE MYSELF?
YOU'RE DOING IT,
SO SAY SOMETHING NICE.
I'M SORRY THAT YOU DIED.
AT LEAST
YOU HAVE EACH OTHER.
YOU'RE TOGETHER.
[MASON]: YOU KNOW,
I DON'T GET IT.
THEY'RE MILLIE'S PARENTS.
THOSE PEOPLE
ARE SUPPOSED TO BE
RELATED TO YOU?
ROUND ROBIN TENNIS BULLSHIT?
THEY'RE RELATED TO MILLIE.
HAPPY TIME MILLIE?
THEY LOOK LIKE DRINKERS.
THEY LOOK
LIKE CATHOLICS.
THEY LOOK LIKE
THEY WOULDN'T LIKE ME.
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY
ABOUT MY FAMILY?
YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M TRYING TO SAY.
I DON'T THINK I CARE
FOR THE IMPLICATION.
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU WANT
THAT FROSTY TENNIS BITCH
TO BE YOUR MOM.
THEY'RE NOT
HER FAMILY.
WHY ARE WE TALKING
ABOUT THEM
AS IF THEY ARE?
IT'S NOT
JUST ABOUT TENNIS.
WELL, THEY DON'T EXIST,
AND THAT'S
A SQUASH RACQUET.
DO YOU PLAY SQUASH?
NO, BUT I THINK
I'D BE GOOD AT.
REALLY?NO.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO
ENLIGHTEN ME AS TO THE
POINT OF THE PICTURE?
EVERYBODY ELSE
HAS PICTURES ON
THEIR DESKS,
AT HAPPY TIME.
I DON'T. I JUST WANT
DELORES OFF MY CASE.
SHE SAYS I DON'T FIT IN.
DELORES IS RIGHT.
IT'S A LITTLE LATE
IN THE GAME TO START.
I DON'T WANT TO FIT IN.
I'M JUST DON'T WANT
TO STAND OUT.
OKAY, I'LL BUY THAT.
HERE YOU GO.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU GUYS FELL FOR THIS
WAFFLE HAUS CLUB CRAP.
SIX MORE PUNCHES,
I GET A FREE WAFFLE.
I'VE ONLY GOT EIGHT
MORE TO GO.
SEVEN, AND I HATE WAFFLES.
YOUR NEXT WAFFLE IS FREE.
I'VE BEEN RAVENOUS LATELY.
IT'S THE WHOLE
"I'M DEAD METABOLISM THING"...
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU SURE YOU DON'T
WANT A CARD?
THANK YOU, KIFFANY,
BUT IT'S REALLY
NOT MY THING.
[GEORGE]:  WHATEVER EVERYONE
ELSE WAS DOING,
I ALWAYS WENT THE OTHER WAY.
I WASN'T A JOINER.
MAYBE THAT'S JUST
THE WAY I WAS BROUGHT UP.
[DOORBELL CHIMING]
[CHRISTMAS CAROLERS SINGING]
♪ OH, HOW THEY POUND
RAISING THE SOUND ♪
♪ O'ER HILL AND DALE
♪ TELLING THEIR TALE
[YOUNG GEORGE HUMMING]
GEORGIA. GEORGIA, SHH.
THEY'LL HEAR YOU.
SWEETIE. SHH.
WHY ARE WE PRETENDING
NOT TO BE HERE?
BECAUSE WE DON'T WANT
THEM COMING BACK
AND SINGING EVERY NIGHT.
THEY'LL WANT US TO JOIN THEM.
OKAY.
GEORGIA,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
GEORGIA, GET BACK HERE!
CLANCY!WAIT.
GEORGE, GET BACK HERE,
OR THERE'LL BE
NO SANTA CLAUS FOR YOU.
YOU DON'T SCARE ME.
♪ MERRY, MERRY CHRISTMAS
♪ FROM EVERYWHERE
FILLING THE AIR ♪
♪ OH, HOW THEY POUND--
SHUT UP!
♪ RAISING THE SOUN...
WE WANT A SILENT NIGHT!
♪ SILENT NIGHT
NO, STOP IT!
♪ HOLY NIGHT
AND NEVER COME BACK!
COAST IS CLEAR.
[CLANCY]:
GOOD JOB, SWEETIE.
THANKS.
[GEORGE]:  AND IT WASN'T
JUST CAROLING.
FACED WITH ANY KIND
OF ACTIVITY,
MY PARENTS WENT THE OTHER WAY.
RAN THE OTHER WAY.
WE WERE A GROUP OF LONERS.
IF THERE WERE OPTIONS,
CHANCES ARE WE'D OPT OUT.
BUT BEING UNDEAD
AND UNMOTIVATED
AT THE WORKPLACE,
I HAD A LOT OF TIME
ON MY HANDS
TO THINK ABOUT
THE WHAT-IFS OF LIFE...
LIKE, WHAT IF I HADN'T
DROPPED OUT OF COLLEGE?
WOULD I STILL HAVE DIED?
WHAT IF I HAD HAD
A DIFFERENT FAMILY,
A FAMILY THAT DIDN'T
ALWAYS OPT OUT?
♪ ...CHRISTMAS IS HERE
♪ MERRY, MERRY, MERRY
MERRY CHRISTMAS ♪
♪ MERRY, MERRY, MERRY, MERRY
CHRISTMAS ♪
AND GOD BLESS US, EVERYONE.
♪ ...FROM EVERYWHERE
FILLING THE AIR ♪
THINK FAST!
I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I CAUGHT YOU OFF-GUARD.
I'M GREGG,
THE RETREAT FACILITATOR.
I'M MILLIE,
JUST MILLIE.
OH, I'M AFRAID
SHE'S NOT WITH US.
I DON'T REALLY PLAY GAMES.
I'M NOT VERY... GAMEY.
YOU KNOW,
EVERYONE HAS SOMETHING
TO CONTRIBUTE TO THE TEAM.
HEY, DON'T YOU WANT TO BE
AT ONE WITH NATURE
AND YOUR
FELLOW WORKERS?
NOPE. CAN'T. BEDWETTER.
OOH, GEE. THAT'S TOO BAD.
I'M KIDDING.
BUT I'M REALLY
NOT GOING.
REALLY.
YOU KNOW, I'M SURE
THAT THIS ONE'LL FIT.
I'M SURE IT'S
YOUR SIZE. JUST...
NOT REALLY A GROUP-HAT
PERSON EITHER.
WELL, YOU'RE NOT
A LOT OF THINGS, ARE YOU?
[GEORGE]:  I'M NOT EVEN ALIVE,
SO LET'S LOSE THE ATTITUDE.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, YOU HAVE
FUN HOLDING DOWN THE FORT.
[GEORGE]:  BUT I DIDN'T WANT
TO HOLD DOWN THE FORT.
THE FORT'S FOR LOSERS.
THE FORT'S A PAIN IN THE ASS.
REGGIE!
DINNER!
I'M COMING.
DID YOU STRAIGHTEN YOUR ROOM?
YES.
DID YOU PUT EVERYTHING AWAY?
YES!
IS IT SPOTLESS?
SPOTLESS.
REGGIE.
WHY ARE YOU UNFOLDING
THAT NAPKIN?
BECAUSE I'M EATING DINNER.
THIS ISN'T FOR US.
THIS IS FOR THE REALTOR
AND THE COUPLE SHE'S
BRINGING BY TOMORROW.
YOU'RE MAKING THEM DINNER?
I'M MAKING IT LOOK
LIKE A DINNER PARTY.
BUYERS WANT
TO SEE A PLACE
WHERE THEY MIGHT
ENTERTAIN.
WE NEVER ENTERTAIN.
WELL, IT'S JUST FOR SHOW.
IT'S LIKE A...
IT'S LIKE
A SERVING SUGGESTION.
WHERE'S OUR DINNER?
I GOT US
BURGER ROUND-UP.
YOU AND I GET TO DO
A PICNIC.
THIS IS BULLSHIT.
PUTTING FOOD ON THE FLOOR
DOESN'T MAKE IT A PICNIC.
PLEASE DON'T SWEAR.
THIS IS HOW
HOMELESS PEOPLE EAT.
WELL, I'M GOING TO ENJOY
MY ROUND-UP WITH CHEESE
WHETHER YOU JOIN ME OR NOT.
NOT.
I'M GOING TO MY ROOM.
YOU'RE SLEEPING WITH
ME TONIGHT.
I ALREADY MADE YOUR BED
AND I WANT IT TO STAY
THAT WAY.
IT'S MY ROOM, AND YOU SNORE.
I MEAN IT, REGGIE!
YOU'D BETTER NOT
BE MESSING UP THAT BED.
I MEAN IT![DOOR SLAMS]
WORK A DOUBLE TODAY?
THAT'S ROUGH.
I DON'T MIND. KEEPS ME
OUT OF TROUBLE.
YOU WANT A PIECE
OF CHERRY PIE, SWEETIE?
SURE.YOU EVER WAIT TABLES?
HARDER THAN DIGGING A DITCH.
YOU SHOULD TRY IT
AND SEE WHAT A REAL JOB IS.
IT IS A NOBLE VOCATION.
MY DOGS ARE BARKING.
I HAVE A REAL JOB,
I HAVE TWO REAL JOBS.
SO I THINK
I'M GONNA GO ON
THE HAPPY TIME
RETREAT TOMORROW.
PIE'S NICE.
DID YOU HEAR ME?
WHEN I WAS YOUR AGE,
I USED TO TREAT THE CRUST
LIKE IT WAS JUST THERE
TO HOLD THE GOOD STUFF IN.
I USED TO LEAVE
THE WHOLE BACK END OF IT
ON THE PLATE.
BUT AS I GOT OLDER,
I LEARNED TO APPRECIATE CRUST.
STAYING ON THE OUTSIDE,
LOOKING IN,
IT'S NOT REALLY
THE BEST WAY TO LAY LOW.
THE MORE I STAY
OUT OF THE GROUP,
THE MORE THEY NOTICE ME.
THAT'S BAD.
YOU LEARN THAT
THE CRUST AND PIE
ARE TWO VERY
DIFFERENT RECIPES.
ULTIMATELY, THEY CO-MINGLE,
BUT THEY ARE
VERY SEPARATE ENTITIES.
I'M SAYING
I'M GOING TO GO.
IT'S THE RIGHT THING
TO DO, OKAY?
OKAY, YOU'VE DECIDED.
WHAT DO YOU NEED ME FOR?
I NEED THE DAY
OFF TOMORROW.
CAN YOU COVER FOR ME?YOU KNOW, GEORGE,
REAPING ISN'T LIKE
SOME WAITRESS
TRADING SHIFTS.
THE NOBLE VOCATION.
I DON'T NEED
YOUR SMART MOUTH.
THIS IS SERIOUS BUSINESS.
SERIOUS BUSINESS.
I NEED TO KNOW
WHERE YOU ARE.
YOU ARE LIKE
AN E.R. DOCTOR,
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT?
YOU'RE ON CALL.
YOU'RE ON CALL 24/7.
365.I DON'T NEED
YOUR SMART MOUTH.
SORRY.
I CHANGED MY MIND.
WELL, I THINK
THAT'S WISE.
NOT ABOUT THE RETREAT,
ABOUT THE PIE.
SO, UM, I'LL SEE YOU
WHEN I GET BACK.
YOU WANT IT?YEAH, PLEASE.
MORE COFFEE?
PLEASE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
IT'S JUST FOR THE AROMA.
HONEY, THIS COUPLE
IS READY TO PAY MORE
THAN WE'VE EVEN ASKED,
SO LET'S PUT ON
A SHOW HERE.
WHAT KIND OF SHOW?[DOORBELL CHIMES]
A GOOD ONE.
SO LET'S SMILE
AND BE FRIENDLY
AND MAKE THEM
FEEL WELCOME.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
MAKE THE COOKIES?
REGGIE, GET THE DOOR.
OH, HEY.
LET ME ASK YOU
SOMETHING, MILLIE.
WOULD YOU SCREW
A MUSTANG GRILL
TO A '57 CHEVY?
ME? NO.EXACTLY.
YOU DON'T MESS
WITH A CLASSIC.
SO WHEN I SAY,
"GET THE FIXINGS
FOR S'MORES,"
YOU DON'T SHOW UP
WITH ANY OLD CHOCOLATE BAR.
THE S'MORE IS LIKE
A DELICATE ECOSYSTEM--
GRAHAM CRACKER,
MARSHMALLOW,
AND THE GREAT AMERICAN
HERSHEY BAR.
I'M SORRY.
I'M NOT A CAMPER.
HEY, I'M REALLY HAPPY
YOU DECIDED TO JOIN US,
MILLIE.
YOU JUST NEED TO GET
YOUR HEAD IN THE GAME.
COME ON.
[DOG BARKING]
BACK IN THE TRUCK.
GO ON.
FUCKING MUTT.
THE GREAT OUTDOORS.
BRISK.
MM.
FEEL THAT?
THAT'S THE I.Q. FALLING.
GODDAMNED DOG
WOULD JUST AS SOON
FUCK A DUCK
THAN HUNT ONE.
I MEANT TO SAY,
"GO, TEAM,
HERSHEY BARS OR BUST."
ALTHOUGH I DON'T CARE
FOR THE CRUELTY TO ANIMALS.
THEY'RE HUNTERS.
HERSHEY BARS?
AH.
NICE 12-GAUGE.
DADDY HAD ONE OF THOSE.EXCUSE ME.
FULL CHOKE.
IS IT DUCK-HUNTING
SEASON ALREADY?
YEAH, WHATEVER.
HEY, WEIGHT-LOSS
DRINKS, HUH?
MOST HUNTERS
ARE MORNING PEOPLE.
THEY HAVE HERSHEY BARS.
THAT'S WHAT I LIKE
TO HEAR, MILLIE.
LET'S LOAD 'EM UP.
HI, LINDA.
OH, GREAT BOOTS.
THANK YOU.
JOY, THESE ARE THE COPES,
ANDY AND STEPHANIE.
HI.HI.
THIS IS REGGIE.
HELLO.
GREAT PLACE.
ARE YOU BAKING?
I AM.
THE COPES
ARE VERY INTERESTED
IN THIS PROPERTY.
AS YOU CAN SEE,
THEY'RE IN NEED
OF A LITTLE MORE SPACE.
WELL, EVER SINCE
SHE GOT, UH,
OR SINCE WE GOT...
YOU KNOW.
I NEVER KNOW EXACTLY
HOW TO SAY IT.
SAY, "SINCE
I IMPREGNATED HER."
TAKE FULL RESPONSIBILITY.
UNLESS, OF COURSE,
IT'S NOT YOURS.
JUST, UH, LOOK
AT THE PERIOD TREASURES
THAT THEY HAVE PRESERVED...
ALL OF THE CROWN MOLDINGS,
THE ORIGINAL HARDWARE.
NICE.
MODERN AMENITIES AS WELL.
THESE ARE ALL
DUAL-PANE WINDOWS.
I INSISTED ON THOSE
FOR SAFETY.
I WAS PREGNANT
WITH MY DAUGHTER
WHEN WE BOUGHT
THE HOUSE.
AND I'M GUESSING
THAT'S YOU.
GUESS AGAIN.
THAT WAS HER SISTER.
GEORGE.
GEORGE?
GEORGIA.
OH. PRETTY NAME.
THIS REALLY IS
THE PERFECT HOME
FOR A GROWING FAMILY.
REGGIE, WHY DON'T YOU
SHOW THE COPES YOUR ROOM?
DO I GET A COMMISSION?REGGIE!
I'D LOVE IT
IF YOU WOULD TAKE US TO
SEE YOUR ROOM, REGGIE.
OKAY...
VERY INTERESTED.
FOR YOU.
YOU.
ROUTE 9
AND GENTILLY BOULEVARD.
SLIPPERY PETE'S.
BIG BIKER HOTSPOT.
YOU NEED AN ESCORT,
LET ME KNOW.
YOU'RE VERY SWEET,
BUT I CAN HANDLE MYSELF.
WELL, THEY'RE BIKERS,
NOT VAMPIRES, DAISY.
DON'T LET THE BLONDE
LOCKS DECEIVE YOU.
I'M A VERY POWERFUL WOMAN.
WELL, GOOD FOR YOU.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO
TAKE A LITTLE TIME OFF TODAY,
AND BY LITTLE,
I MEAN I WILL
BE BACK TOMORROW,
AND I TRUST YOU WILL BE
FINE WITHOUT ME,
AND BY THAT,
I MEAN TRY NOT TO FUCK UP.
BY FUCK UP, OF COURSE,
I MEAN MASON.
YOUR SERVANT.
WELL, I HAVE ORDER
TO RESTORE.
YOUR SERVANT.
FIRST TIME, CUTE.
SECOND TIME, YOU HAVE
TO BUY ME SOMETHING.
WELL, WHY DO YOU ASSUME
I'M GOING TO FUCK UP?
BECAUSE YOU'RE A FUCK-UP!
THIS, OF COURSE,
IS THE PERFECT
CHILDREN'S ROOM.
PLENTY OF SPACE
FOR MORE BEDS,
IF MORE KIDS
ARE IN GOD'S PLAN.
I DON'T SEE
HOW GOD'S INVOLVED.
[LAUGHING]
[CELLPHONE RINGS]
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK. YES?
THE ONLY MOLD IN THAT HOUSE
IS BETWEEN HER EARS.
GRIMM'S ANTHOLOGY.
I USED TO BE
A TEACHER, YOU KNOW?
I WAS SUPPOSED
TO PUT THAT AWAY.
THAT'S OKAY.
IT'S A DELIGHTFUL ROOM.
WHERE'S YOUR
SISTER'S BEDROOM?
MY MOM TURNED IT
INTO AN EXERCISE ROOM.
OH.
WHERE'S YOUR SISTER
LIVING NOW?
I DON'T KNOW, EXACTLY.
IS SHE IN COLLEGE?
SHE'S DEAD.
OH...
I'M SO SORRY.
IT'S OKAY.
SHE'S NOT, LIKE,
COMPLETELY GONE.
BECAUSE...
SHE COMES BACK.
SHE COMES BACK?
A LOT.
[WIND BLOWING]
[GASPS]
THAT WASN'T HER.
[GREGG]: OKAY, EVERYBODY,
IF YOU COULD BE AN ANIMAL,
ANY ANIMAL,
WHAT ANIMAL
WOULD YOU CHOOSE TO BE?
DELORES,
WOULD YOU LIKE TO GO FIRST?
OH, I'D LIKE TO GO LAST,
IF YOU WOULDN'T MIND.
OKAY, I THINK
THAT'D BE APPROPRIATE.
THANKS, GREGG.
MILLIE,
HOW ABOUT YOU?
I THINK I'LL GO
RIGHT BEFORE DELORES.
DO YOU THINK
THAT'S APPROPRIATE?
[GEORGE]:  WHO GIVES A SHIT?
I REALLY DO, GREGG.
CAN I START?
SURE, TODD.
YEAH,
THAT'D BE GREAT.
IF I WERE AN ANIMAL,
I THINK I WOULD BE A CRAB.
NOT AN ANIMAL.
MILLIE.
WELL, IT'S NOT.
IT'S A CRUSTACEAN.
WHAT?
WELL, AT LEAST I'M LISTENING.
I'M SORRY.
A CRAB'S AN ANIMAL.
IT'S A BIG, FURRY,
WARM-BLOODED BEAST
THAT SLEEPS IN COCKTAIL SAUCE.
MILLIE, THIS IS AN EXERCISE
ABOUT REVEALING YOURSELF
TO YOUR CO-WORKERS.
NOW, WE ALL FIND
THINGS TO HIDE BEHIND
AT THE OFFICE.
YOU KNOW, OUR CUBICLES,
OUR TELEPHONES,
OUR DEADLINES...
OUR SARCASM.
WE ALL FIND WAYS
NOT TO GET TO KNOW
THE PEOPLE
THAT WE RELY ON THE MOST.
OUT HERE IN THE WILD,
THERE'S NO PLACE
TO HIDE, OKAY?
SO I THINK THAT WE SHOULD ALL
TRY TO GET TO KNOW
TODD THE CRAB.
WHOO-HOO!
[GEORGE]:
I BET TODD HAS CRABS.
TODD, PLEASE.
I ALWAYS FEEL...
AS IF I'M MOVING SIDEWAYS.
MOTHERFUCKING...
I AM VICIOUSLY FUCKED.
BASTARD HELL...
NO, NOT YOU, DARLING.
UNLESS YOU'RE INTERESTED,
IN WHICH CASE--
NO? WELL, PISS OFF, THEN.
FUCK OFF. OH, JESUS CHRIST.
OH, BOLLOCKS.
KIFFANY! KIFFANY.
HEY, THERE.
LISTEN, HAVE YOU FOUND
A LITTLE POST-IT?
YOU KNOW,
THE LITTLE YELLOW ONES
WITH WRITING ON?
LIKE THE KIND YOU PEOPLE
ALWAYS PLAY WITH?
YES, YES, YES.
EXACTLY. EXACTLY.
NO. IS THIS ONE
PARTICULARLY IMPORTANT?
I DON'T BOLLOCKING
WELL KNOW, DO I?
JESUS CHRIST, I AM FUCKED.
MOVE.
SHIT. BOLLOCKS.
FUCKING BOLLOCKS!
OKAY, WELL, THAT'S IT.
I'M FUCKING FUCKED, AREN'T I?
I'M BOLLOCKING
VICIOUSLY FUCKED.
ROYALLY FUCKED, I AM.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
WELL, THAT IS
MOST INTERESTING.
I JUST ASSUMED
ALL THOSE STORIES
ABOUT DEGRADING
INITIATION RITUALS WERE TRUE.
NO ONE HAS TO KILL ANYONE
TO GET INTO THE BALD EAGLES.
WE FIGURE
THE RIGHT MEMBERS
COME AT THE RIGHT TIME.
TREACH HERE BECAME ONE
AFTER SOMEONE HAD READ A POEM
HE WROTE IN A BIKER MAG.
OPEN VERSE
FOR THE OPEN ROAD.
HEAR, HEAR.
[ALL]: HEAR!
I DO LOVE A REAL MAN
OF LETTERS.
SO WHY ARE YOU GUYS
CALLED THE BALD EAGLES?
WE DON'T WEAR HELMETS.
FUCKS WITH OUR HAIR.
I JUST THINK
A MAN SHOULD CHOOSE
HOW CLOSE TO DEATH
HE WANTS TO LIVE.
CLOSER THAN YOU THINK, TINY.
DAISY, DAISY,
I NEED YOUR HELP.
NOW.
YOU WANT TO TAKE YOUR--
YOU WANT TO TAKE YOUR
HANDS OFF THE LADY?
I'M IN TROUBLE.
THIS IS MASON.
HE'S OKAY, FELLAS,
JUST NOT VERY WELL
BROUGHT UP IS ALL.
NO, I'M NOT.
THE ONLY THING WE HATE
WORSE THAN BAD MANNERS
IS THE GODDAMN
FASCIST HELMET LAW.
BARE HEADS TILL WE'RE DEAD.
TILL WE'RE DEAD!
BARE HEADS.
YEAH! YEAH!YEAH, RIGHT, RIGHT,
RIGHT, RIGHT.
BETTER DEAD THAN NOT.
WHAT?
I LOST MY POST-IT.
HAVE A NICE RIDE, FELLOWS.
GOT TO GO.
SUCH A LOYAL GROUP OF PEOPLE.
BUT SO DANGEROUS.
[PATRONS YELLING]
TINY!
THOSE MOTORCYCLES,
THEY'RE DANGEROUS.
WELL, A HELMET
WOULDN'T HAVE HELPED.
TINY MADE A BIG MESS.
...AND I MOVED HERE
FROM ALBANY
WHEN SHE BROKE OFF
THE ENGAGEMENT.
3,000 MILES
DOWN THE ROAD,
AND I STILL CAN'T GET HER
OUT OF MY MIND.
NO.
WE WERE NEVER ENGAGED, FRANK.
WE WERE TOTALLY ENGAGED.
I GAVE YOU MY MOTHER'S RING.
SO?
OKAY, FRANK, FRANK,
FRANK, FRANK!
SALLY, PLEASE.
RIGHT. RIGHT.
ANYWAY, THAT'S WHY
I FEEL LIKE A LEOPARD.
BECAUSE YOU'RE STALKING HER?
BECAUSE I CAN'T
CHANGE MY SPOTS.
OKAY, MILLIE,
I THINK
IT'S YOUR TURN.
UH, NO, I...
I JUST, I--
I DON'T REALLY...
I'M NOT AN ANIMAL.
[GEORGE]:  THIS WAS STARTING
TO FEEL FAMILIAR...
STAYING ON THE SIDELINES.
CRITICIZING.
CLINGING TO THE FRINGES
INSTEAD OF JUMPING
INTO THE FRAY.
IT WAS LIKE WATCHING
THE ESCALATOR RUN.
WHEN WOULD I STEP ON?
OKAY, DELORES,
WELL, I GUESS
THAT JUST LEAVES YOU.
BRING US HOME.
WELL, UM,
I'VE ALWAYS THOUGHT--
I'M A CAT.
I MEAN, NOT LIKE A HOUSE CAT.
NOT LIKE MURRAY, DELORES.
I'M A STRAY...
WANDERS THE STREETS, ALONE,
KIND OF DISTANT AND MEAN.
NOT A CAT YOU'D WANT TO PET
OR BRING HOME TO YOUR KIDS.
YOU JUST DON'T KNOW
WHERE THOSE CLAWS ARE,
YOU KNOW.
AND I'M A BLACK CAT.
AND I HAVE MANY, MANY LIVES.
AND NOW YOU KNOW
WHO I AM.
YOU'D THINK
HE'D HAVE A BETTER LOCK.
[DAISY]: WOW.
COLOR ME IMPRESSED.
WELL, IF HE WRITES
THE INFORMATION
ON OUR POST-ITS,
HE MUST COPY IT DOWN
FROM SOMEWHERE, RIGHT?
YEAH, BUT WHERE?
I'LL CHECK
THE LIQUOR CABINET,
YOU CHECK
EVERYWHERE ELSE.
MASON, NO.
THIS IS A COVERT OPERATION.
WE NEED TO TREAD GENTLY
AND COVER OUR TRACKS.
[SNIFFING]
MM...
OLD FARTS LIKE RUBE
ALWAYS HAVE THE BEST BOOZE.
THEY'VE BEEN DRINKING
LONG ENOUGH
NOT TO MESS AROUND
WITH THE CHEAP SHIT.
HOW IS THAT HELPING?
TAKES OFF THE EDGE.
I'M ALL EDGES RIGHT NOW.
ALL RIGHT?
MASON, IF HE FINDS OUT
WE WERE RUMMAGING
AROUND HERE--
PUT THAT DOWN.
PUT IT DOWN.
PUT THAT... DOWN.
THIS WAS YOUR IDEA, DAISY.
I ONCE HAD TO HIDE
FOR HOURS IN ONE
HALF THIS SIZE
FROM THE SHREW
OF A MRS. TYRONE POWERS,
WHO WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
IN PALM SPRINGS.
I WAS FORCED TO URINATE
IN A HIGHBALL GLASS.
WHAT IS IT WITH YOU
AND THE MARRIED ONES?
FORBIDDEN FRUIT?
THAT WAS THEN,
AND I DON'T KNOW WHY
YOU'RE TREATING THIS
LIKE HAPPY HOUR.
OH, SHIT.
SO...
SO MANY OF THEM.
SO MUCH MORE OF IT.
POUR ME A DRINK, WILL YOU?
JUST ONE. AND ONLY
TO WARM ME UP.
YEAH, IT'LL LUBE OUR SYNAPSES
UP A BIT,
MAKE OUR MINDS
A BIT MORE N... NIMBLE.
WE'LL KEEP LOOKING
FOR YOUR POST-IT.
WE'LL-- WE'LL KEEP
LOOKING. YEAH.
WHY ARE YOU SPYING ON ME?
I'M NOT.I WASN'T
SAYING ANYTHING.
I DIDN'T SAY
THAT YOU WERE.
WELL, WHY ARE YOU
HERE, THEN?
WHY DID YOU SHOW UP
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
WELL, WHAT HAS BEEN
YOUR EXPERIENCE
AS TO WHY I SHOW UP
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
OH, NO.
YOU KNOW,
YOU DO HAVE
ACTUAL RESPONSIBILITIES
IN THIS WORLD.
I KNOW YOU.
YOU'RE MILLIE'S SPONSOR.
SO DEVOTED.
DELORES, RIGHT?RIGHT. AND YOU'RE RUBE.
I AM.
IS THAT A FIRST NAME
OR LAST NAME?
JUST RUBE.
LIKE CHER.
LIKE HOUDINI.
LOVE HOUDINI.
WOULDN'T IT HAVE BEEN FUN
TO HAVE SEEN HIM?
[GEORGE]:  SEEN HIM?
RUBE PROBABLY REAPED HIM.
WHAT BRINGS YOU
OUT HERE, RUBE?
WELL, DELORES...
AS MUCH AS I'D LIKE
TO GET INTO THAT WITH YOU--
UH-HUH?
ONE OF THE "A"S OF A.A.
STANDS FOR--
YOU DON'T WANT A DRINK,
DO YOU, MILLIE?
ACTUALLY, I WAS REFERRING
TO THE OTHER "A".
OH, OF COURSE.
DELORES,
I THINK I NEED
TO GO FOR A WALK
AND GET SOME FRESH AIR.
WELL, YOU'RE
IN THE WOODS.
YOU'RE SURROUNDED
BY FRESH AIR.
I JUST...
WANT TO GO FOR A WALK.
I NEED TO...
COMMUNE WITH
THE SPIRITS OF THE NORTHWEST.
YOU ARE A CAT, AREN'T YOU?
ALONE AND MYSTERIOUS.
MAKE SURE YOU MAKE IT BACK
FOR GHOST STORIES AND S'MORES.
I'LL TRY.
YOU DON'T HAPPEN TO
KNOW ANY GHOST STORIES,
DO YOU, RUBE?
UH, I'VE HEARD
A COUPLE IN MY DAY.OH, HOW FUN.
[GEORGE]:  AND JUST AS I
WAS GETTING COMFORTABLE
IN THE CIRCLE,
DEATH PULLED ME AWAY.
[SINGING ALONG WITH RECORD]:
♪ YOU PUT YOUR LEFT ARM IN
♪ YOU PUT YOUR LEFT ARM OUT
YOU PUT YOUR LEFT ARM IN ♪
♪ AND YOU SHAKE IT ALL ABOUT
♪ YOU DO THE HOKEY POKEY
AND YOU TURN YOURSELF AROUND ♪
♪ THAT'S WHAT
IT'S ALL ABOUT ♪
WHOO!
[RECORD CONTINUES PLAYING]
♪ YOU TAKE
YOUR RIGHT ELBOW OUT ♪
♪ YOU PUT YOUR
RIGHT ELBOW IN ♪
♪ AND YOU SHAKE IT
ALL ABOUT-- ♪
I FEEL LIKE A FLAPPER.
YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN ME
DO THE CHARLESTON.
YOU ARE LOVELY.
OPERA... OPERA...
JAZZ...
BORING, BORING, SNORING.
I AM DRUNK.
I HATE BEING DRUNK.
FUNNY,
I DON'T MIND IT.
EVER.
MY GOODNESS.
YOU THINK YOU KNOW A MAN--
BARRY MANILOW.
PLAY ME
SOMETHING SWINGING.
I WANT TO DANCE
AND FORGET ALL THIS...
THIS STUFF.
OH, YEAH,
BECAUSE YOU KNOW...
SOMEBODY'S GOING TO DIE ALONE
TODAY, AREN'T THEY?
WHAT WAS ON YOUR
POST-IT, MASON?
NOW, CAN I SHOW YOU
THE OUTSIDE STORAGE?
I'D LOVE TO SEE THAT.
HONEY?
IN A SECOND, I JUST
WANT TO GET A FEEL
FOR THE HOUSE
ONE MORE TIME.
OKAY.
[T.V. PLAYING]
[SHUTS T.V. OFF]
SO, REGGIE,
WHAT WERE YOU WATCHING?
NOTHING.
WHAT'D YOU MEAN
WHEN YOU SAID
YOUR SISTER COMES BACK?
SHE VISITS US.
AND YOU TALK TO HER?
NOT LIKE FACE TO FACE.
SO SHE CHECKS UP ON YOU,
SEES IF YOU'RE OKAY?
I GUESS.
ARE YOU?
I DON'T THINK
YOU SHOULD MOVE HERE.
WHERE WAS HER FAVORITE SPOT
IN THE HOUSE?
HER ROOM, I THINK.
SHE DIDN'T REALLY
TELL ME THINGS.
I THINK WE SHOULD GO BACK
TO THE WAFFLE HAUS.
IF YOU MISS A REAP,
A WRATH WILL BE
VISITED UPON YOU
AS SUCH WILL HAVE
YOU WRITHING
IN TESTICLE-SHRIVELING HORROR.
THAT WAS RUBE.
WHY DO YOU
DRINK SO MUCH?
YOU'RE SO LOVELY.
I LOVE YOU.
YOU'RE SO PERFECT,
AND YOUR SKIN
IS JUST SO BEAUTIFUL.
TRUE, BUT NOT WHAT I ASKED.
IT'S PEOPLE'S IMPERFECTIONS
THAT MAKE THEM SO BEAUTIFUL.
LIKE BLACK VELVET
THAT SHOWS OFF
A LITTLE DIAMOND.
THOSE THREE FRECKLES
THAT SHOW OFF
YOUR ALABASTER SKIN.
CUT THE BULLSHIT, MASON.
WHAT, DAISY?
REALLY, WHAT,
IN THE WHOLE GODDAMN
SCHEME OF THINGS,
IS ONE MORE UNHAPPY SOUL?
I JUST CANNOT CARE ANYMORE.
I CANNOT CARE ANYMORE.
YOU SAW THE POST-IT
BEFORE YOU LOST IT.
NO.
YES, YOU DID.
YOU ALWAYS LOOK AT IT
WHEN YOU GET IT,
EVEN FOR JUST A SECOND.
NO, I DON'T.
DO I?
I WATCH YOU.
YOU NEVER JUST PUT IT
IN YOUR POCKET.
DO YOU WATCH ME?
YOU ALWAYS LOOK AT IT,
BECAUSE YOU'RE CURIOUS.
YOU WANT TO KNOW.
WHAT DO I WANT
TO KNOW?
THEIR NAME.
WHERE THEY'RE
GOING TO DIE.
YOU'RE CURIOUS.
YOU ALWAYS
LOOK AT IT.
YEAH.
SOMETIMES,
I DO LOOK AT IT.
AND YOU LOOKED
AT THIS ONE, TOO.
AND THIS PERSON
WON'T DIE ALONE.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
THIS IS A GHOST STORY,
AND IT'S A LOVE STORY.
IT'S ABOUT A MAN
WHO LOVED A WOMAN.
A MAN WHO THOUGHT
THE FLAME OF THEIR LOVE
COULD NEVER DIMINISH.
BUT IT DID.
WHAT HAD ONCE BEEN A DANCE
HAD BECOME...
A BATTLE.
THEY FOUGHT AND FOUGHT.
IN THE DEAD OF NIGHT,
AFTER ANGRY WORDS
WERE SPOKEN...
HE LEFT THEIR BED
AND SADDLED HIS HORSE.
AND SHE SAID TO HIM,
"IF YOU DON'T COME BACK
IN THREE DAYS,
"THEN YOU CAN
NEVER COME BACK.
"MARK MY WORDS...
I'LL BE GONE."
WELL, WHERE WOULD SHE GO?
TO LIVE WITH
AN OLD BOYFRIEND
FROM HIGH SCHOOL?
I THINK YOU TWO ARE
A LITTLE AHEAD OF THE STORY.
AM I GOING TO BE
INTERRUPTED AGAIN?
ANY OTHER QUESTIONS,
THOUGHTS?
QUERIES?
THEN I WILL CONTINUE.
STILL ANGRY...
STILL ANGRY,
THE MAN RODE AWAY...
AND HE ENJOYED THE SOLITUDE.
THE NOISE OF THEIR ARGUMENT
WAS REPLACED
BY THE SOOTHING SOUNDS
OF THE FOREST.
[TWIGS SNAPPING]
BUT AFTER JUST TWO DAYS
IN THE FOREST,
HE GREW LONELY.
HE WAS FILLED WITH REGRET.
HE WANTED TO RETURN
TO THE WOMAN HE LOVED,
AND HE WANTED TO RETURN
TO THE LIFE THAT HE MISSED.
HE FOUND A SHORTCUT
THROUGH THE WOODS,
AND HE TOOK IT.
HE WAS DESPERATE,
DESPERATE TO GET BACK
TO THE WOMAN HE LOVED
BEFORE IT WAS TOO LATE.
HER THREATS RANG IN HIS HEAD.
WOULD SHE WAIT FOR HIM?
OR WOULD SHE BE TRUE
TO HER WORDS?
WOULD SHE BE GONE?
HE COULD FEEL HIS HORSE
LOSING SPEED,
AS IF IT WOULDN'T MAKE IT
THROUGH THE NIGHT.
[DOG BARKING]
[GUNSHOT]
WHAT WAS THAT?
DOUBLE-BARREL 12-GAUGE,
FULL CHOKE.
DO WE NEED TO GO
AND HELP SOMEBODY?
THAT WAS SWEET, FRANK.
I'M JUST A STORYTELLER.
GREGG HERE'S
IN CHARGE. GREGG?
OH, HO... NO.
NO, I-I-I DON'T THINK SO.
I'M A LITTLE AFRAID
OF THE TREES AT NIGHT.
WELL, WE CAN EITHER
STOP NOW OR GO ON
WITH THE STORY.
IT'S UP TO YOU GUYS.
NO MORE
INTERRUPTIONS. HMM?
OKAY?
HOW YOU DOING, CRYSTAL?
YOU'RE ABOUT TO LOSE
YOUR MARSHMALLOW.
THE MAN CAME TO THE EDGE
OF A DARK AND UNKNOWN SWAMP.
HE HAD TO MAKE A DECISION.
SHOULD HE GO
INTO THE SWAMP
OR GO AROUND IT?
DOES HE GO THROUGH THE SWAMP
OR DOES HE GO AROUND IT?
WE ALL ASK OURSELVES
THAT QUESTION, DON'T WE?
IT'S A VERY SCARY QUESTION
TO ANSWER ALL ALONE.
EXCUSE ME. EXCUSE ME.
YOU'VE GOT
SOMETHING I NEED.
I'M SORRY?THE POST-IT.
IT'S MINE.
I NEED IT.
THEN MAYBE
YOU CAN TELL ME
WHY IT HAS
MY NAME ON IT.
I CAN'T DO THAT.
I'M SORRY.
[RUBE]:  AND NEXT TO
THE SWAMP WAS A BOY.
MY NAME IS...
HEY!
[RUBE]:  THE MAN ASKS THE BOY,
"TELL ME, DOES THE SWAMP
HAVE A HARD BOTTOM?"
[GUNSHOT]
AND THE BOY TELLS
THE MAN IT DOES.
SO THE MAN GUIDES HIS HORSE
INTO THE SWAMP.
[DOG WHIMPERING]
AND AS HE BEGINS TO SINK
DEEPER AND DEEPER
INTO THE SWAMP,
HE SAYS TO THE BOY,
"I THOUGHT YOU SAID
IT HAD A HARD BOTTOM."
AND THE BOY SAYS, "IT DOES."
"YOU'RE JUST NOT THERE YET."
SO THE MAN DOESN'T GET BACK
TO HIS WIFE IN TIME?
HE MIGHT.
HE MIGHT GET OUT
AND REACH HER, RIGHT?
THAT'S THE END
OF THE STORY, FOLKS.
I MEAN, HE MIGHT
GET BACK TO HER.
GUYS...
HI. WHAT DID I MISS?
A WONDERFUL STORY.
MILLIE, I'VE BEEN WORRIED
ABOUT YOU.
WE HEARD A GUNSHOT, AND--
OH, I'M FINE.
OKAY.
JUST DON'T GO OFF ALONE
LIKE THAT AGAIN.
RUBE?
THANK YOU.THANK YOU.
SO, WAS THE STORY
YOU TOLD SCARY?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
I DIDN'T HEAR IT,
I JUST TOLD IT.
SMART MOUTH.
I THINK IT WAS
A LITTLE SCARY.
YOU KNOW WHY PEOPLE
LIKE TO GET TOGETHER
TO HEAR THESE KINDS
OF STORIES IN THE WOODS?
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME?
THEY LIKE
TO FACE THEIR FEARS...
TOGETHER.
IT'S SOMEHOW EASIER
THAN FACING THEM ALONE.
WOULD YOU LIKE
A "SOME"?A WHAT?
IT'S WHAT I'VE CHRISTENED
THE COMBINATION
OF GRAHAM CRACKER
AND CHOCOLATE,
LIGHTLY TOASTED
OVER AN OPEN FLAME.
WE'RE OUT OF MARSHMALLOWS.
"SOME"?
AH, IT'S BETTER THAN NOTHING.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
YOU'RE NOT STAYING?
OH, I'VE GOT AN EARLY
BREAKFAST MEETING.
YOU ENJOY THE REST
OF THE RETREAT.
[GEORGE]:  MAYBE IT WAS JUST
THE WARMTH OF THE FIRE,
BUT FOR ONCE, I WAS HAPPY
TO HAVE A SPOT IN THE CIRCLE.
DELORES AND I
DROVE BACK TOGETHER,
AND SHE TOLD ME
THAT SHE, TOO, WAS A CAT.
THAT SHE WAS BORN
IN THE YEAR OF THE CAT,
THAT SHE HAD ALL
THE QUALITIES OF A CAT.
I SWEAR TO GOD,
IF SHE TOLD ME
SHE WENT IN A LITTER BOX,
I WAS LEAVING HER
BY THE SIDE OF THE ROAD.
[DELORES]: ANYWAY...
LOOKS GOOD.
MORE BUYERS COMING?
NO. THIS IS FOR US.
I THOUGHT WE DESERVED
A LITTLE SIT-DOWN
BREAKFAST.
[CAR HORN HONKING]
SORRY. I'VE GOT TO GO.
OH, UH, WAIT.
UM, HERE. TAKE BACON.
YOU KNOW, REGGIE,
IF YOU EVER WANT
TO TALK TO ME
ABOUT ANYTHING,
YOU KNOW...
I MEAN,
ANYTHING AT ALL,
ABOUT GEORGE...
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
HELLO?
AW, COME ON.
IF ANYONE IS THERE,
WOULD YOU JUST SAY
SOMETHING?
FINE.
YOU KNOW,
IF THAT KEEPS HAPPENING,
I'M GOING TO CHANGE
OUR NUMBER.
I DON'T THINK
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
I'VE GOT TO GO.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
[CAR ENGINE STARTING]
[GEORGE]:  ONCE UPON A TIME,
THERE WAS A GIRL NAMED GEORGE,
WHO COULDN'T QUITE FORGET
THERE WAS ONCE UPON A TIME.
[♪♪]