[♪♪]
[GEORGE]:  MOST GIRLS MY AGE
ARE OBSESSED WITH
PRETTY SIMILAR THINGS...
FUN THINGS.
SOME ARE OBSESSED
WITH FLIRTING...
SOMETHING MORE THAN FLIRTING.
SOME ARE OBSESSED
WITH THEIR RIDE...
OR WHETHER TO WEAR
REALLY RUBY RED
OR SILVER CITY PINK.
[SIREN BLARING]
ME, I WAS OBSESSED, TOO.
I WAS OBSESSED
WITH POST-ITS...
POST-ITS AND DEATH.
I WAS BEYOND OBSESSED.
[KNOCKING]
DID YOU WRITE MY NAME
ON MY POST-IT?
WHAT?
DID YOU WRITE MY NAME
ON MY POST-IT?
THE ONE WHERE I DIED?
GEORGIA, I'M NOT
A BIG FAN OF THE DROP-BY.
WELL, I WANT TO KNOW.
THE DROP-BY,
IT'S A DISCOURTESY.
POLITE SOCIETY
HAS A PROTOCOL,
AN AGREED-UPON
TIME AND PLACE.
YOU MAKE PLANS.
KIND OF LIKE A POST-IT.
I WAS IN THE MIDDLE
OF A SENTENCE
WHEN YOU KNOCKED,
A WRITTEN SENTENCE
IN A BOOK.
I HAD TO PUT IT DOWN
'CAUSE YOU KNOCKED.
I WAS IN THE MIDDLE
OF SOMETHING
WHEN YOU KNOCKED.
DOES IT MATTER
WHO WROTE YOUR POST-IT?
HERE'S WHAT I KNOW.
YOU GET A LIST OF NAMES,
AND YOU TRANSFER
THE FIRST INITIAL,
LAST NAME,
TIME AND PLACE
ONTO A POST-IT.
BUT YOU GET MORE THAN THAT.
THAT'S RIGHT.
WHAT ELSE DO YOU GET?
IS MY NAME STILL
IN HERE SOMEWHERE?
WHAT ELSE DOES IT
SAY ABOUT ME?
OH, WHAT IS THIS?
LIKE, SANTA CLAUS'S LIST?
DOES IT SAY WHO'S BAD
AND WHO'S GOOD?
DOES IT SAY THAT
I WAS 18 YEARS OLD?
THAT I HAD NEVER
HAD A BOYFRIEND?
THAT I DIDN'T EVEN HAVE
MY DRIVER'S LICENSE?
DID IT SAY THAT
I HAD NEVER
DONE ANYTHING?
YOU KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT PERSIAN MYTHOLOGY?
PERSIAN MYTHOLOGY SAYS,
ON THE LAST DAY,
THERE'S A RECKONING.
THERE'S AN
OLD-FASHIONED SCALE.
YOU GOT ONE SIDE FOR LIGHT,
ONE SIDE FOR DARKNESS.
GOOD, EVIL.
EVERYBODY STEPS ONTO THE PAN,
SEES HOW THEY MEASURE UP.
THE WORLD WANTS IT ALL
TO MAKE SENSE,
THE WORLD WANTS IT
ALL TO ADD UP.
THE WORLD WANTS BALANCE.
THIS IS YOUR RESPONSE?
SOME STORY
ABOUT SOME BULLSHIT
WAY STATION INTO
THE AFTERLIFE?
YOU'RE STILL HERE, GEORGE.
I WANT TO BE
YOUNG AND SILLY.
YOU ARE YOUNG AND SILLY.
GEORGIA, I WROTE
YOUR NAME
ON THAT POST-IT.
I HADN'T MET YOU.
I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT A GREAT KID YOU WERE...
BUT IF I HAD KNOWN YOU,
I STILL WOULD'VE WRITTEN
YOUR NAME ON THE POST-IT.
THAT'S THE WAY OF THE WORLD.
[GEORGE]:  I THINK HE'S WRONG.
I DON'T THINK IT
ALL "ADDS UP."
I DON'T THINK
ANY OF IT MAKES SENSE.
I DON'T SEE ANY
FUCKING BALANCE ANYWHERE.
LET ME DOWN!
IT'S ALL ABOUT LUCK.
EITHER YOU'RE LUCKY,
OR YOU'RE NOT...
AND I'M NOT.
THIS IS BULLSHIT.
SHE SOLD
THE SLATERS' HOUSE.
SHE GOT 50,000
OVER ASKING.
ALL RIGHT, SHE'S THEIR
TOP REALTOR, CLANCY.
SHE'S AMBITIOUS
AND RUTHLESS,
RIGHT UP YOUR ALLEY.
I THINK
REGGIE'S UPSTAIRS.
REGGIE?
REGGIE!
I CAN'T FIND HER... BYE.
I DON'T SEE WHY
WE HAVE TO SELL
THE HOUSE.
WELL, HONEY, HALF OF IT
IS YOUR FATHER'S.
CAN'T WE JUST
BUY HIS HALF?
I DON'T HAVE
THAT KIND OF MONEY.
THEN I GUESS
YOU'LL HAVE TO
GO BACK TO WORK.
REGGIE, GOING BACK
TO WORK, YOU KNOW,
WOULD REQUIRE
A MAJOR LIFESTYLE
CHANGE FOR ME,
YOU KNOW,
FOR BOTH OF US.
SO I HAVE TO LIVE
IN SOME CHEESY APARTMENT
JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE LAZY?
[SIGHS]
BUT DO YOU REMEMBER
WHAT MY JOB WAS?
SECRETARY.LEGAL SECRETARY,
AND LAWYERS
ARE VERY ANGRY PEOPLE.
DON'T YOU REMEMBER
HOW INCREDIBLY
UNHAPPY I WAS
WHEN I CAME HOME?
YOU'RE ALWAYS
INCREDIBLY UNHAPPY.
NO, I'M NOT.
UNHAPPY
IN A CHEESY APARTMENT.
UNHAPPY IN A BIG HOUSE.
EXCUSE ME, CAN I BORROW
YOUR SALT, PLEASE?
THANK YOU.
ROXY...
CAN I SEE YOUR NEW
POLICE REVOLVER, PLEASE?
NO.
PLEASE?
I JUST WANT TO
HOLD IT, ROXY.
NO.
LOOK, I WON'T SHOOT IT.
I PROMISE, PROMISE, PROMISE.
I JUST WANT TO FEEL IT
IN MY HANDS, YOU KNOW?
PLEASE!NO, AND STOP ASKING ME.
GIVE ME THE GUN.
YOU ARE REALLY WORKING
MY NERVES THIS MORNING.
YOU DON'T HAVE THE  HUEVOS.
YOU WISH YOU HAD
A PAIR LIKE MINE, BABY.
AND A GUN LIKE THAT.
HERE'S YOUR JUICE,
HON.
THANKS.
IS IT TOO MUCH TO ASK
TO EAT MY EGGS IN PEACE?
JUST LET THE LITTLE MAN
HOLD THE GUN.
[EXHALES]
[GEORGE]:  LUCK'S EVERYWHERE,
JUST DRIFTING IN THE BREEZE,
AND THE BAD LUCK
THAT'S FLOATING AROUND
HAS TO LAND ON SOMEBODY,
AND WHOEVER IT LANDS ON...
WELL, PEOPLE FIND WAYS
TO EVEN THE SCORE.
[CAT YOWLING]
[APPLAUSE]
[GONG]
MY PARENTS ARE
SELLING MY HOUSE.
DO YOU WANT
ANYTHING, SWEETIE?NO, THANKS.
THE HOUSE I GREW UP IN,
THEY'RE SELLING IT.
HOW MUCH?I HAVE NO IDEA.
HOW MUCH IS THE CHECK?
WHY WOULD THEY DO THIS?
THEY LOVED OUR HOUSE.
IT JUST DOESN'T... ADD UP.ADD UP.
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
WE LIVED THERE
FOR 20 YEARS.
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM
WITH THE CHECK?
SHE DIDN'T CHARGE US ENOUGH.LET'S PAY IT AND RUN.
WE MOST CERTAINLY
WILL NOT.
GREAT. "JOHNNY LAW
ON-THE-SPOT."
THEY ARE JUST UP
AND LEAVING.
SHE DIDN'T CHARGE ME
FOR MY FRUIT SALAD.
THAT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.[ROXY]: IT MAKES SENSE.
COPS EAT FREE.
IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE
HER PARENTS ARE MOVING.
THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
MAYBE IT'S JUST TOO
PAINFUL FOR THEM
TO WALK BY YOUR
BEDROOM EVERY DAY.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE
THEY NEED THE EXTRA SPACE,
BECAUSE WHEN
SHE KICKED THE BUCKET,
THEY GAINED AN EXTRA ROOM.
ROXY, DO ME A FAVOR.
SHOOT HIM.
GLADLY.
I AM SO FAR AHEAD
OF THIS BIT.
I WAS JOKING.
ROXY?[MASON]: LOOK AT YOU.
YOU THINK YOU'RE
SO BLOODY SPECIAL,
DON'T YOU?
PRANCING AROUND
IN YOUR TIGHT
BLUE TROUSERS
AND YOUR BIG SHINY GUN.
WELL, LET ME TELL YOU
SOMETHING, SWEETHEART.
COPS DON'T EAT FREE.
PEOPLE HATE COPS.
[GEORGE]: PLEASE DON'T.
I'VE HAD A BAD MORNING
ALREADY.
UH, EXCUSE ME?
KIFFANY?
COULD YOU SETTLE
A DISPUTE FOR US?WHAT IS IT, SWEETHEART?
DO OFFICERS OF THE LAW
RECEIVE COMPLIMENTARY MEALS?
NO.[MASON SNICKERS]
COFFEE'S FREE.
DO YOU WANT
SOME MORE COFFEE?
NO, THANK YOU.
SO, WHAT?
YOU JUST NEGLECTED
TO CHARGE HER
FOR HER FRUIT SALAD?
WELL... LOOK AT THAT.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'LL GET YOU
A NEW CHECK.
JESUS CHRIST!
[MASON WHIMPERING]
FUCKING HELL!
SO THEY'RE SELLING
YOUR CHILDHOOD HOME?
YEAH.
THAT'S A SHAME, SWEETIE.
IT'S NOT FAIR.
THAT FUCKING HURT.
IT DOES HURT.
SOMETIMES THE WORLD
JUST DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
[THUD]
PARDON ME.
HEY, CAN I GET A SODA?
[HONKING]
[SCREAMING]
[THUD]
FIVE-LETTER WORD,
"ACCIDENTAL FISH."
FLUKE.
[MASON]: TIME TO GENERATE
A NEW REVENUE STREAM.
BEHOLD.
[GEORGE]: OH, MASON,
MASON, MASON.
ARE YOU DRINKING
AGAIN?
NO.
SAY, "AS GOD
IS MY WITNESS."
I DON'T BELIEVE IN GOD.
NOW, WHAT ABOUT
A LITTLE WAGER?
COME ON,
GUESS WHERE THE PEA IS.
WHERE IS THE PEA?
PUT A DOLLAR DOWN.
COME ON.
A GEORGIE WASHINGTON
FROM GEORGIE GIRL.
IS IT UNDER THIS ONE?
COULD IT BE UNDER THIS ONE?
OR IS IT THIS ONE?
WHERE COULD IT BE?
WHERE IS THE PEA?
GUESS,
AND WIN A DOLLAR.
THE MIDDLE ONE.
NOPE.[GEORGE]: OH!
BY GEORGE,
SHE'S GOT IT.
YEAH, YOU ARE
DRINKING AGAIN.
OKAY, SO GIVE ME
THE MONEY BACK,
AND WE'LL START
ALL AGAIN.
MM... NO.
YES, BECAUSE THAT
WAS PRACTICE, ALL RIGHT?
AND YOU JUST LOST A DOLLAR.
MORNING,
BOYS AND GIRLS.
HOW'S EVERYBODY?
HAVING A LOVELY DAY,
THANK YOU.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
YOU STILL WEARING
THOSE STICKS, HUH?I AM.
YOU FIND YOURSELF
A CROSS,
AND SUDDENLY
YOU'RE A CATHOLIC?
IT THINK IT LOOKS
VERY PRETTY ON ME,
DON'T YOU?
YOU KNOW, GEORGE,
YOU HAVE YOUR
VERY OWN SAINT.
I'D RATHER HAVE A PONY.
SAINT GEORGE
IS THE PATRON SAINT
OF FARMERS, SOLDIERS,
BOY SCOUTS,
CAVALRY, CHIVALRY,
AND ENGLAND.
I WANT A SAINT.
HAVE I GOT A SAINT?
YES, SAINT THOMAS.
WHAT ABOUT SAINT MASON?
THOMAS IS THE PATRON SAINT
OF MASONS.
THERE IS NO "SAINT MASON,"
BUT SAINTS ARE MARVELOUS.
THERE'S A PATRON SAINT
FOR EVERYTHING.
PATRON SAINTS
FOR LOST CAUSES,
FOR BEING DEPRESSED,
PATRON SAINTS--
FOR BEING BORED
OUT OF YOUR SKULL.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT
THE HOLY TRINITY IS,
GEORGE?
WE ARE IN A FUCKING
RESTAURANT.
IT'S PEPPERS,
ONIONS, AND CELERY.
WOULD A LITTLE RITUAL
IN HER LIFE
DO HER ANY HARM?
I HAVE A LITTLE
RITUAL MYSELF.
LET US BEGIN.
NOTHING FOR ME?NOT UNLESS
YOU GOT ONE
UNDER ONE OF YOUR
PRETTY LITTLE SHELLS.
DON'T YOU USUALLY
RIDE YOUR BIKE
OVER HERE?
YES.DID YOU RIDE IT TODAY?
YES.WELL, IT'S NOT OUT THERE.
WHAT?YOUR BIKE IS GONE.
I GAVE YOU
THAT BIKE.
THIS BETTER BE A JOKE.
IS IT REALLY GONE?
LET ME SEE
YOUR VERSION
OF THE SHELL GAME.
I COULD REALLY
USE A LAUGH
THIS MORNING.
WHAT?[MOCKING MASON]: "WHAT?"
[DAISY LAUGHS]
[RUBE]: COME ON,
QUIT FUCKING AROUND.
PLAY.
[YELLING OBSCENITIES]
[SCREAMING]
SOMEONE STOLE MY BIKE!
[RECORD NEEDLE SCRATCHING]
[ORDER BELL DINGS]
[MAN]: ORDER UP.
SOMEONE STOLE MY BIKE.WE GOT THAT.
DID YOU LOCK IT?
YES, I LOCKED IT.
ALL THEY LEFT
IS ONE TIRE.
WHICH TIRE?
THE TIRE THAT WAS LOCKED.
I HAD A FEELING
YOU'D LOSE THAT BIKE.
YOU'VE GOT TO MAKE
A FIGURE-EIGHT
WITH YOUR HANDS.
[MASON]: YOU DON'T
HAVE TO BE SO
HUFFY ABOUT IT.
I'VE LOST MY PEA NOW.
WHAT?
YOU'RE BLAMING ME?
WELL, WHEN SOMETHING
IS LOST,
SOMEONE HAS TO BE BLAMED,
ISN'T THAT THE THEORY?
IF NOT YOU,
THEN WHO?
THE DESIGNER OF THE BIKE
FOR MAKING SOMETHING
SO BEAUTIFUL
THAT SOMEONE ELSE COVETS IT?
OR MAYBE WE SHOULD BLAME ME?
MAYBE WE SHOULD ASSIGN
NO BLAME AT ALL?
AS DAISY'S PEOPLE WOULD SAY,
"HE GIVETH, HE TAKETH AWAY".
I'D BLAME THE GUY
WHO TOOK IT.
[MASON]: I'D GET REVENGE.
YOU KNOW, AN EYE FOR AN EYE,
A  SCHWINNFOR A  SCHWINN--
I WOULD STEAL
SOMEBODY ELSE'S BIKE.
THAT'S A BAD IDEA.
OKAY, ROXY'S BIG,
BAD, AND BLUE.
NOW, WHY DON'T
YOU ASK HER?
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
RUBE, CAN I BORROW
YOUR TRUCK?
ARE YOU
A RESPONSIBLE DRIVER?
I AM AN
EXCELLENT DRIVER.
I PROMISE TO TAKE CARE
OF YOUR PIECE-OF-SHIT TRUCK.
WELL, THAT'S NOT
THE RESPONSE
I WAS LOOKING FOR.
FINE.
[RUBE]: GEORGE.
WHAT?
SOMETIMES PRETTY THINGS
JUST DISAPPEAR.
WELL, I GUESS
THAT'S JUST MY BAD LUCK.
SHOW ME THE HANDS.
WINNER OR LOSER,
WINNER OR LOSER.
WHICH WILL IT BE?
ONLY TIME WILL TELL.
HERE TODAY,
GONE IN A MOMENT.
IT'S UNDER THE MIDDLE ONE.
[REGGIE]: IT'S SQUISHY.
I'M GOING TO
SQUISH YOU TWO
IF YOU GET ANY CLAY
ON THAT TABLE.
WE'LL CLEAN IT.
YEAH, I'VE HEARD
THAT ONE BEFORE.
YOU KNOW, GEORGE,
WHEN YOU'RE
ALL GROWN UP,
YOU ARE NOT
GOING TO BELIEVE
HOW LITTLE YOU WERE.
I'M NOT LITTLE.
REGGIE'S LITTLE.
YOUR FATHER
WAS KIDDING, HONEY.
YOU'RE A BIG GIRL.
[REGGIE]: UH-OH.
OKAY, LET'S DO
THE LEFT ONE.
[GEORGE]:  THE WORLD
MAY TRY TO MESS WITH YOU.
OUT THERE, IT MAY BE
A FREE-FOR-ALL,
BUT IN HERE,
THERE'S A SYSTEM IN PLACE
TO ADDRESS THAT.
NEXT.
MAYBE IT'S JUST
THE UNIFORMS, BUT IN HERE,
IT FEELS LIKE
THERE'S ORDER IN THE WORLD.
NEXT.
AND IF YOU JUST GET
THE FACTS ONTO THE BOOKS,
ODDS ARE, THE SYSTEM
TAKES CARE OF YOU.
HI.
I'D LIKE TO REPORT
THE THEFT OF MY BICYCLE.
IT HAPPENED
ALMOST AN HOUR AGO,
ON BAY STREET.
FILL THIS OUT.
WHAT'S THIS?
IT'S A HARVARD LAW DEGREE.
WE'RE ALL
VERY PROUD OF YOU.
LISTEN, I'M GOING TO BE
REALLY LATE FOR WORK.
CAN I JUST DESCRIBE
THE BIKE TO YOU,
AND YOU COULD PUT OUT
AN A.P.B. OR WHATEVER?
NO.
GREAT.
EXCUSE ME.
THANK YOU.
HOLY SHIT.
DID YOU JUST SEE THIS?MM-HMM.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOU, DEAR?
SOMEONE...
STOLE MY BIKE,
AND IT WAS
A REALLY COOL BIKE.
A MAN FONDLED
MY BEHIND
ON A CITY BUS.
THERE'S NO EXCUSE
FOR THAT.
NONE.
I THINK
HE WAS STABBED.
YEP. "ASSAULT WITH
A DEADLY WEAPON,
KNITTING--
NEEDLES."
THE SHITHEAD
HAD IT COMING.
HERE WE GO,
HERE WE GO.
HERE WE GO, WHERE WE GO...
WHERE WE GO, NOBODY KNOWS.
THAT'S YOUR PATTER?
PATTER'S BULLSHIT.
PATTER'S HOW
YOU DRAW PEOPLE IN.
PEOPLE ARE DRAWN IN
BY THE GAME...
AND BY MY NON-THREATENING
GOOD LOOKS.
WELL.
THE PATTER SEDUCES.
IT'S NOT
YOUR STRONG SUIT.
THERE.
DO YOU KNOW WHY PEOPLE
PLAY THE SHELL GAME?
BECAUSE THEY THINK
THEY CAN BEAT THE ODDS.WRONG.
THEY THINK
THEY CAN BEAT YOU.
THEY'RE SMARTER THAN YOU.
IN THIS CASE,
THEY'RE RIGHT.
I'M SMARTER THAN YOU THINK.
ARE YOU SMART ENOUGH
TO PLAY STUPID?
I AM SO SMART,
I'M PRACTICALLY RETARDED.
ARE YOU DRINKING AGAIN?NO.
ARE YOU LYING?AS GOD IS MY WITNESS.
NOW, WHERE'S THE PEA?
FOLLOW THE PEA.
FIVE'LL GET YOU TEN,
TEN'LL GET YOU TWENTY,
FIFTY'LL GET YOU A HUNDRED.
DOUBLE YOUR MONEY,
JUST CATCH IT ONCE.
ONE TIME, ONE TIME,
ONE TIME.
YOU NEED A RHYTHM.
YOU NEED TO HYPNOTIZE
WITH YOUR WORDS.
MM-MM.
I CAN HYPNOTIZE WITH
MY CAT-LIKE MOVEMENT.
NOW, HOW SLICK WAS THAT?
THERE'S ONLY ONE MOVEMENT
I CARE ABOUT.
IT HAPPENS EVERY DAY
RIGHT ABOUT NOW,
AND THERE'S NOTHING
CAT-LIKE ABOUT IT.
IT'S UNDER THE ONE
ON THE RIGHT.
WRONG.
MY RIGHT.
I CAN DO THIS.
[SIGHS]
[CLEARS THROAT]
HOW IS THIS
LOW PRIORITY?
IT'S PETTY THEFT,
MISS.
IT'S A VICTIMLESS CRIME.
VICTIMLESS?
THEN WHO THE FUCK AM I?
AND THE LANGUAGE
WON'T MAKE IT
A HIGHER PRIORITY.
DID I WIN ANYTHING?
20 SCRATCH-OFFS,
AND I DIDN'T GET SQUAT?
WHAT ARE THE ODDS?
WHO DO I HAVE TO KILL
TO GET SOME ATTENTION
AROUND HERE?
IT'S JUST AN EXPRESSION.
I'LL CATCH UP
WITH YOU GUYS.
I'LL TAKE IT
FROM HERE, THANKS.
THANK GOD.
YOU HAVE TO HELP ME, ROXY.
IT WAS A YELLOW BIKE--
I CAN READ.
AND IT HAD A BELL,
AND A MISSING TIRE.
GEORGE,
I WILL TREAT THIS
WITH THE RESPECT
IT DESERVES.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
LOOK, I'M HAPPY
TO FILE A REPORT,
I'M HAPPY TO FOLLOW UP,
BUT DON'T EXPECT
ANYONE AROUND HERE
TO LOOK OUT
FOR YOUR BIKE.
SOMEBODY BROKE THE LAW.
SOMEBODY HAS TO PAY.
YOU'RE ON THE BOOKS, GEORGE.
[GEORGE]:  I'M ON THE BOOKS,
BUT THE BOOKS
DON'T REALLY GIVE A SHIT.
IN THE END,
THE LESSON
THE SYSTEM TEACHES YOU
IS PRETTY SIMPLE...
YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN.
WHAT THE HELL?
IS IT SATURDAY?
[WOMAN]:
NO, ALL-STAFF MEETING.
HOW COME
YOU'RE NOT THERE?
PHONES.
"T.H.E.F.T."
"THIEVES HARM
EVERYONE'S FUN TIMES."
LET'S BREAK IT DOWN, PEOPLE.
WHAT DO I MEAN
WHEN I SAY HARM?
HARM WHO? YOU?
OR THE CUTIE
IN THE NEXT CUBICLE?
THE C.E.O.,
THE PRESIDENT,
EVERYONE
DOWN THE CHAIN--
SOMEONE STOLE MY BIKE.
AND EVERYONE IN HERE
IS A THIEF
UNTIL PROVEN OTHERWISE...
INCLUDING YOU.
FREAK.OH, DID I MISS A JOKE?
LET ME
TELL YOU SOMETHING.
STEALING COMPANY
PROPERTY IS NO JOKE.
PEOPLE THINK,
"OH, THE COMPANY
IS SUCKING AWAY MY LIFE.
I'LL JUST TAKE
SOMETHING BACK."
WHO IS THIS GUY?
SECURITY EXPERT,
BECAUSE OF ALL
THE SUPPLY THEFT.
I DIDN'T GIVE YOU
A PROMOTION
SO YOU'D SHOW UP
AN HOUR LATE.
I WAS TRYING
TO FIND MY BIKE
SO I COULD GET HERE.
YOU. WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
[GEORGE]: MILLIE.
YOU LIKE YOUR
LIFE HERE, MILLIE?
[GEORGE]:  NOT SO MUCH.
TELL HIM YOU'RE HAPPY.I'M REALLY HAPPY.
GOOD.
GOOD, BECAUSE YOU KNOW
WHAT PEOPLE DO
WHEN THEY'RE UNHAPPY,
DON'T YOU?
THEY... GET A CAT?
NOT YOU.[MAN]: WRONG.
THEY TAKE STAPLES...
OR ROLLER-BALL PENS...
OR POST-ITS.
PEOPLE WHO DON'T
LIKE THEIR LIVES
TRY TO GET EVEN,
AND THAT MAKES HAPPY TIME
AN UNHAPPY PLACE.
[GEORGE]:  NO MATTER HOW
I TRIED TO PLAY THE GAME,
IT WASN'T COMING OUT
IN MY FAVOR.
DIE, BECOME REAPER,
SEE FAMILY SELL HOUSE,
SEE BIKE GET STOLEN,
DO NOT PASS "GO".
"R.I.P.O.F"
"REPORT...
"IDENTIFY...
"PROVE...
"OSTRACIZE...
FIRE."
"RIP OF?"
YOU GOT A PROBLEM THERE,
MILLIE?
YOU MISSPELLED
"RIP-OFF".
DROPPED AN "F."OH, I SEE.
WE HAVE OURSELVES
A SMART-ASS.
DON'T YOU MEAN,
"SMART AS"?
[DELORES]: SHH, MILLIE.
LET ME TELL YOU
SOMETHING THERE, MILLIE.
I CAN'T SING.
I CAN'T TAP-DANCE.
I CAN'T TWIRL A RIFLE.
I HAVE ONE TALENT,
MILLIE.
I FIRE TROUBLEMAKERS.
I FIND TROUBLEMAKERS,
AND I FIRE THEM.
THAT'S MY TALENT, MILLIE.
WHAT'S YOURS?
[GEORGE]:  YOU DON'T
WANT TO FIND OUT.
WATCH THIS ONE.
I DON'T LIKE HER.
R-I-P-O-F.
FIGURE IT OUT,
LEST YOU CATCH THE BULL
BY THE HORNS.
UH, WELL, UM,
THERE'S, UM, MUFFINS.
[MASON]: DO YOU FEEL
LUCKY TODAY?
WHERE IS THE PEA?
FIND THE PEA.
[MAN]: THE PEA IS UNDER...
THIS SHELL.
JUST TAKE THE MONEY.
TAKE THE MONEY.
GO AWAY.
HOW'S THAT REVENUE
STREAM RUNNING?
IT'S GOING REALLY WELL,
ACTUALLY, REALLY WELL.
I'VE ACTUALLY SAVED YOU
SOMETHING FROM THE EARNINGS.
UH, HANG ON, WHERE IS IT?
HANG ON, LET ME FIND IT.
IT'S THERE.
[JOY]: NEW CAR?OH...
UM, YEAH, IT'S,
UM, IT'S A LEASE.
IT LOOKS LIKE
A REAL CHICK-MAGNET.
[CLANCY]: WHERE'S REGGIE?
SHE'S AT SCHOOL.
YOU KNOW,
THE PLACE THEY KEEP
THE NON-VOTERS
FOR EIGHT HOURS A DAY,
KEEP THEM
OUT OF TROUBLE.YEAH, I... I...
I KNEW THAT.
I WAS JUST NERVOUS
ABOUT COMING OVER HERE.
SO...
WHERE DO WE START?
1983.
THAT WAS A JOKE.
HA.
OH, I REMEMBER THIS.
I STOLE THIS
FROM THAT HOTEL ON MAUI.
WE WERE BOTH
SMOKING ON THAT TRIP.
[JOY]: AND DRINKING.
THAT WAS A GOOD VACATION.
THE BEST.
WELL, SINCE I STOLE IT,
I GUESS IT'S MINE.
[GEORGE]:  THAT'S RIGHT,
I'M THE THIEF.
I'M THE CAT-BURGLAR.
DON'T YOU EYEBALL ME.
OH, YEAH, LIKE ANYONE
WANTS YOUR FAKE PRADA TOTE.
OKAY, DEATH WAITS FOR NO MAN.
GOT TO GO, GOT TO GO.
[DELORES]: MILLIE!
YOU WERE
AN HOUR LATE,
AND YOU'RE GOING
SOMEWHERE ALREADY?
[GEORGE]:  GOD, I'VE WORKED
THIS 12-STEP EXCUSE
INTO THE GROUND.
SOMETHING ELSE, PLEASE.
DELORES,
I DIED ABOUT A YEAR AGO,
AND BECAME A GRIM REAPER...
AND SOMEONE
AT THE WOODSIDE MALL
IS GOING TO DIE
IN ABOUT 20 MINUTES,
PROBABLY VIOLENTLY,
AND I HAVE TO GO
TAKE THEIR SOUL
BEFORE THEY BITE IT.
WELL, THAT'S DEATH FOR YOU.
I APPRECIATE
YOUR UNDERSTANDING.
THAT SECURITY GUY
REALLY UPSET ME.
THAT WHOLE
"BULL WITH THE HORN" THING,
WHATEVER THAT WAS,
I HAVE NO IDEA,
BUT I'M ON THE EDGE HERE,
DELORES,
AND I NEED TO GO
TO A MEETING.
SAY NO MORE.
"GRANT ME THE SERENITY"--
OKAY, THANK YOU. LATER.
[GEORGE]:
"I'M GOING TO A MEETING."
I'D BORE MYSELF TO DEATH
IF I WEREN'T ALREADY DEAD.
I'M TELLING YOU,
THE  KITCHEN GUILLOTINE
IS THE LAST SLICER
YOU'LL EVER BUY.
YOU LIKE PEPPERS?
IT SLICES PEPPERS.
LOOK AT THAT,
EASY AS PIE.
JUST RIGHT THROUGH
THE PEPPER, LIKE NOTHING.
POP THAT ON THERE,
THROW SOME MEAT
ON THIS BABY,
AND YOU'RE DOING
WHAT I LIKE TO CALL
THE "BOSCACCI HIBACHI TANGO."
I'M XAVIER BOSCACCI,
AND THAT'S FUN
IN THE KITCHEN!
COME ON, PEOPLE.
AND THAT'S...
FUN IN THE KITCHEN.
RIGHT...
FUCKIN' MALL GIGS.
OKAY, I NEED A VOLUNTEER.
HOW ABOUT YOU,
YOUNG LADY?NO.
COME ON, LET'S GIVE HER
A LITTLE ENCOURAGEMENT.
EXCUSE ME.
LOOK, KID, I GOT TO
MOVE FOUR OF THESE
BY THE END OF THE HOUR,
OR I'M A DEAD MAN.
ALL RIGHT?
JUST READ THE SCRIPT.
DO YOU LIKE
FRESH FRUIT JUICE?
I LOVE FRESH FRUIT JUICE.
WELL, LET ME
ASK YOU THIS...
DO YOU LIKE THE RIND?
I THROW THE RIND AWAY.
YOU THROW THE RIND AWAY?
MY FRIEND,
IF YOU'RE NOT
TRYING THE RIND,
YOU'RE NOT LIVING.
[GEORGE]:  NEITHER ARE YOU,
IN THREE MINUTES.
OH, WATCH IT, PAL.
UH...
ISN'T FRESH FRUIT JUICE
EXPENSIVE?
MY FRIEND,
NOT ONLY
IS THE KITCHEN GUILLOTINE
EASY TO USE,
AN--AND...
EASY TO CLEAN,
IT'S ONLY $19.99.
AND YOU, TOO,
CAN HAVE FRESH
MIMOSAS FOREVER.
[CROWD]: OH!
[GEORGE]:  AND THAT'S
FUN IN THE KITCHEN.
YOU GOT SOME JUICE
ON YOUR COAT.
ACTUALLY, THAT'S YOU.
OH.YOU GOT GUILLOTINED.
I KNEW THAT BLADE
WASN'T SAFE.
WE WERE JUST TRYING
TO CUT COSTS, YOU KNOW.
AND THE WORLD GETS EVEN...
AND MAYBE EVEN
THROWS YOU A BONE.
SO, IS THE RIND
REALLY GOOD
FOR YOU?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
THAT IS NOT TRUE, JOY.
[JOY]: I'M SURE OF IT.
I BOUGHT THAT TABLE
WHEN YOU WERE
IN GRAD SCHOOL.
[CLANCY]: YOU KNOW,
OKAY, WHATEVER.
TAKE IT.
DON'T ACT LIKE
YOU'RE GIVING ME
SOMETHING OUT OF CHARITY.
THAT WAS THE AGREEMENT.
I BROUGHT IT IN.
OKAY, FINE.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I BROUGHT IN?
YOUR NECKLACE.
MY...
YOUR MOTHER
GAVE THIS TO ME.MY MOTHER.
I'D THINK THAT FALLS
SQUARELY INTO THE CATEGORY
OF THINGS I BROUGHT
INTO THE MARRIAGE.
SHE'S MY MOTHER.
YOU SHOULD GIVE
THE NECKLACE BACK TO ME.
DON'T YOU GET IT?
I WANTED TO GIVE THIS TO--
I WANT TO GIVE THIS
TO OUR DAUGHTER.
[CLANCY]: WELL, I CAN
GIVE IT TO HER
JUST AS EASILY.
YOU WANT IT, CLANCY?
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
RIP IT OFF MY NECK.
[DOOR SLAMS][J.D. BARKS]
HI, SWEETIE.
HEY, REG.
[JOY]: HOW WAS SCHOOL
TODAY, HONEY?
DID I DO ONE OF THESE?[CLANCY]: YEAH, YOU DID.
RIGHT, JOY?
WELL, WHERE IS IT?
[JOY]: I DON'T KNOW, SWEETIE.
IT MIGHT HAVE
GOTTEN LOST SOMEWHERE.
I NEED A RIDE
TO MY DRUM LESSON...
[CLANCY]: OH, I'LL TAKE YOU.
MOM.
LISTEN, DO YOU MIND
IF I STAY
AND GO THROUGH SOME THINGS?
I REALLY DO.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[GEORGE]:  RUBE SAYS
THE WORLD WANTS BALANCE.
I SAY I'M READY
TO HELP THE WORLD GET IT.
[REMOTE BEEPS]
WHY SHOULDN'T I GET MINE?
EVEN IF I DIDN'T
EXACTLY PAY FOR IT.
[BEEP]
WHO ARE YOU KIDDING?
YOU'RE NOT THIS LUCKY.
[BEEP][HONKS]
THAT'S COOL.
[BEEP]
WHY SHOULD I PLAY
BY THE RULES?
IT'S NOT LIKE ANYONE
WAS KEEPING SCORE...
[TIRES SQUEALING]
AND MORE IMPORTANT,
IT'S NOT LIKE
ANYONE WAS WATCHING.
[BELL JINGLES]
HI THERE.
JUST BROWSING.
I'VE GOT JESUS CHRIST,
CRYSTAL,
TWIN TOWERS, THERE.
HMM.
TELL ME ABOUT
THE CROSSES.
WHAT WOULD YOU
LIKE TO KNOW?
ARE YOU A COLLECTOR?
NO, THEY JUST SORT OF, UH,
HAVE A HABIT
OF TURNING UP.
YOU WANT TO SEE
SOMETHING PRETTY?
[STRUGGLING]
[GRUNTING]
SEE?
NOW, THERE'S SOMETHING
REALLY PRETTY.
THE CROSSES,
HOW MUCH ARE THEY WORTH?
DEPENDS.ON?
KARAT, AGE, DESIGN.
YOU BUYING?
NO, JUST INFORMATION
GATHERING FOR NOW,
BUT I REALLY DO
FANCY THEM.
THAT'S A NICE PIECE
YOU'VE GOT ON.
IS IT?
MAY I?
YEAH.
EDWARDIAN...
PROBABLY
TURN OF THE CENTURY.
I'LL GIVE YOU
A THOUSAND BUCKS FOR IT.
REALLY?SURE.
I GET GOOD TURNOVER
ON THESE
HEIRLOOM ESTATE PIECES.
I DON'T THINK SO.
ARE YOU CATHOLIC?
A LITTLE BIT.
SO ARE YOU RUSTY?
YEAH, I'M A LITTLE
OUT OF PRACTICE,
BUT YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE DOING.
NOT EVEN A CHUCKLE?
IS RUSTY YOUR REAL NAME?
NO. I HAD RED HAIR
WHEN I WAS A KID.
MY REAL NAME'S JOHN.JOHN WHAT?
JOHN McCOLLUM.
$1,200, BUT THAT'S
MY FINAL OFFER.
NO, THANK YOU.
I THINK I CAN GET
A BETTER DEAL
SOMEWHERE ELSE.
YOU HAVE
BEAUTIFUL THINGS, RUSTY.
RUSTY AND BEAUTIFUL.
"RUSTY AND BEAUTIFUL."
OH![CRASHING]
TAKE THE MIRROR.
REALLY?
FROM ONE CATHOLIC
TO ANOTHER.
YOU KNOW, I ACTUALLY
HAVE PLENTY OF MIRRORS,
BUT I WOULD LOVE
ANOTHER CROSS.
HELP YOURSELF.
YOU'RE A SWEET MAN, RUSTY.
I'M SURE THERE'S A NICE DEAL
WAITING OUT THERE FOR YOU.
[MASON]: YOU DON'T
EAT THE RIND?
THE RIND'S THE BEST PART,
DARLING. LOOK.
THAT'S FUN
IN THE KITCHEN.
ALL RIGHT, YOU KNOW WHAT,
YOU SEE, YOU...
YOU ARE SERIOUSLY BEGINNING
TO CREEP ME OUT,
SO PISS OFF.
GO ON, I MEAN IT.
PISS OFF. SHOO.
GO, GO, GO,
GO, GO, GO.
ANYWAY, YOU LOVELY PEOPLE,
COME AND GET
YOUR KITCHEN GUILLOTINE.
IT SLICES, IT DICES,
IT'LL CUT YOUR FUCKING
HAND OFF IF YOU WANT IT TO.
ONLY 10 BUCKS A POP.
LOVELY, THANK YOU.
BE THE FIRST ON YOUR BLOCK.
BLOODY HELL, I'M GOOD AT THIS.
[MAN]: ME, TOO.LOVELY.
YOUR KITCHEN
GUILLOTINE, SIR.
[GEORGE]:  A DAY OF FIRSTS.
FIRST TIME YOU'VE PULLED
INTO THIS DRIVEWAY
SINCE YOU DIED,
FIRST TIME YOU WALK IN
WITHOUT BREAKING IN,
AND MAYBE THE LAST TIME
YOU SEE THE PLACE.
[WOMAN]: HI.
YOU MUST BE MILLIE.
HI.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
I HAVE TO SAY,
IT'S A REAL COUP
WHEN A HOUSE ON THIS BLOCK
COMES UP FOR SALE.
MOST PEOPLE
KEEP THESE GEMS
IN THE FAMILY
FOR YEARS.
IT'S A VERY SPECIAL
OPPORTUNITY.
AND YOU'RE SURE
THE FAMILY WON'T
BE HERE, RIGHT?
OH, NO, NO,
OF COURSE NOT.
NO, I THINK
IT'S KIND OF, UM,
I DON'T KNOW, CREEPY
HAVING THE FAMILY
HOVERING AROUND
WHEN YOU'RE LOOKING
AT THEIR THINGS.
CREEPY MIGHT BE
TOO STRONG A WORD.
NO, IT'S GOOD.
SO, YOU ARE,
UH, SINGLE?
ENGAGED.
TO A BANKER.
HE'S AT THE BANK
MAKING SERIOUS BANK.
SO THEN FINANCING--
IS THE LEAST
OF OUR PROBLEMS.
WELL, I THINK
IT'S NICE
THAT THE TWO OF YOU
ARE INTERESTED
IN A FAMILY HOME
LIKE THIS.
PREPARING
FOR THE FUTURE...
[GEORGE]:  WHAT I WAS
REALLY DOING, OF COURSE,
WAS FACING MY PAST.
NOW, WHAT'S SPECIAL
ABOUT THE DESIGN
OF THE INTERIOR
OF THIS HOME
IS THE FLOW.
WHY ARE THEY MOVING?
EXCUSE ME?
WHERE IS
THE FAMILY GOING?
OH, I WOULDN'T
KNOW THAT.
WELL, WHY ARE THEY LEAVING?
OH, WELL,
THERE IS NO PROBLEM
WITH THE HOUSE ITSELF.
I CAN ASSURE YOU OF THAT.
NO, NO,
THIS PLACE HAS BEEN
PERFECTLY MAINTAINED.
THE MOTHER IS...
WELL, SHE'S VERY
PARTICULAR. MM.
IT JUST DOESN'T...
MAKE ANY SENSE.[WOMAN]: NO.
I SHOULDN'T TELL YOU THIS,
BUT... THEY LOST A CHILD.
OH, IT WAS VERY SAD.
TERRIBLE ACCIDENT.
NOT IN THE HOME,
OF COURSE,
BUT I THINK THAT WAS
THE BEGINNING OF IT.
THE BEGINNING OF WHAT?
THE END OF THE MARRIAGE.
IT'S VERY COMMON.
MOST MARRIAGES
CAN'T SURVIVE
THE DEATH
OF A CHILD.
I DO LOVE
THOSE DOORS, THOUGH.
[GEORGE]:  AND JUST
AS I DID AS A CHILD,
WHEN FACED WITH SOMETHING
I DIDN'T WANT TO HEAR...
I HEADED STRAIGHT
FOR MY ROOM.
[WOMAN]: CAN I SHOW YOU
ONE OF THE BEDROOMS, THEN?
OH, UM, THAT'S
A TRICKY HANDLE.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO--
...LIFT IT A BIT.
IT'S THE ONLY REAL FLAW
IN AN OTHERWISE
MINT-CONDITION HOUSE,
I CAN ASSURE YOU.
I THINK I'D JUST LIKE
TO GET A FEEL
FOR IT UP HERE...
BY MYSELF.
OH, SURE.
I'LL BE DOWNSTAIRS.
[GEORGE]:  BUT IT WASN'T
EVEN MY ROOM ANYMORE.
MY PARENTS WERE
GETTING A DIVORCE,
AND I DIDN'T EVEN
HAVE A BED TO CRY ON.
WHAT IS IT ABOUT
THE DEATH OF SOMETHING
THAT MAKES PEOPLE
JUST WANT TO
PUT IT IN A BOX?
AND FINALLY,
THERE I WAS...
BUT THERE WAS
NO PLACE FOR ME.
I JUST DIDN'T FIT.
DID MILLIE
EVER COME BACK?
I WANTED HER
TO DO THIS TONIGHT.
[WOMAN]: JUST DON'T SING
"WE ARE THE WORLD"AGAIN.
POUR ONE
APPLE MARTINI
IN YOU,
AND IT'S 1983.
DELORES, DO YOU
WANT TO COME
TO THE KARAOKE
HAPPY HOUR WITH US?
OH, I CAN'T. I'VE GOT
RESPONSIBILITIES.
OH, COME ON, DELORES.
EVERYONE'S
GOING TO BE THERE.
WELL, BACK TO
THE SALT MINES.
[GEORGE]:  ROCK-STAR PARKING.
LUCKY ME.
[♪♪]
[RUBE]: WHAT'S THAT?A MUSTANG.
TEMPS MUST BE
DOING REALLY WELL
IN THIS NEW ECONOMY.
DID YOU STEAL IT?NOT EXACTLY.
DID YOU BUY IT?
HMM, NOT EXACTLY.
WELL, HOW'D YOU
GET IT, EXACTLY?
I THINK I WAS
SUPPOSED TO GET IT.
THAT WHOLE BALANCE THING.
I HAD A REALLY
BAD DAY, RUBE.
I THINK I WAS
SUPPOSED TO GET IT.
OKAY.
SEEN THIS KID TODAY,
THIS MORNING,
LOUIS PICK,
19 YEARS OLD.
HE STOLE $17,
WAS KILLED
RUNNING AWAY.
HE'S NOT A BAD GUY.
NEVER STOLE
ANYTHING IN HIS LIFE.
HE WAS JUST HUNGRY.
HE WAS 19, YOU WERE 18.
WHAT ELSE DID IT SAY
ABOUT ME, ON THE LIST,
BEFORE YOU WROTE MY NAME
ON THE POST-IT?
IT SAID THAT YOU DID NOT
HAVE A DRIVER'S LICENSE.
AND YOU DIDN'T
GET THAT CAR
'CAUSE SOMEONE
STOLE YOUR BIKE.
WHAT HAPPENED TODAY?
MY PARENTS
ARE GETTING A DIVORCE.
LOOKING TO BLAME
SOMEONE FOR THAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
SWEETHEART?
MY EXPERIENCE,
THE DEATH OF A CHILD
DOESN'T KILL A MARRIAGE.
SOMETIMES IT GIVES IT
AN OVERDUE BURIAL,
BUT YOU CAN BLAME
YOURSELF IF YOU WANT TO.
THAT, YOUNG LADY,
WOULD BE UNFAIR.
SEE YOU TOMORROW?
DO ME A FAVOR?
BRING MY FRIEND A BOWL
OF CHOCOLATE ICE CREAM.
[GEORGE]:  TONIGHT,
SOMEWHERE ELSE,
MAYBE THERE'S
A DIFFERENT GIRL
WHO'S DODGING A BULLET,
OR STEPPING
OUT OF THE PATH
OF A SPEEDING TRAIN,
A GIRL WHO'S LUCKY.
I DON'T KNOW...
I FIGURED THAT SINCE
I HIT A PRETTY HARSH
STRETCH OF BAD LUCK
WHEN I WAS 18,
YOU KNOW, THAT WHOLE
"TOILET SEAT FALLING
FROM THE SKY
AND INCINERATING ME"
KIND OF BAD LUCK,
I FIGURED
IT WOULD BE REASONABLE
TO EXPECT A CHANGE
OF FORTUNE
ON THE OTHER SIDE.
WHY SHOULDN'T I GET
THE BOOKS TO BALANCE?
WHY SHOULDN'T I
MAKE THINGS ADD UP?
I'M TIRED
OF PLAYING BY THE RULES.
I WANT TO BE BAD.
I WANT TO HAVE FUN.
I WANT TO KEEP
STEALING BACK PIECES
FROM WHERE MY LIFE
USED TO BE.
I'M JUST LIKE
EVERYONE ELSE...
AND I'M READY
TO EVEN THE SCORE.