[GEORGE]  WHEN I WAS A KID,
I TOOK BALLROOM DANCING.
MY MOM SAID
IT WOULD STAY
WITH ME FOR LIFE,
BUT ALL I REMEMBER IS,
"ONE, TWO, THREE,
ONE, TWO, THREE."
WHAT DO YOU MEAN NO
BLUEBERRY PANCAKES?
THEY'RE SEASONAL.
WELL, EXPLAIN SOMETHING TO ME.
ARE THE BLUEBERRIES FRESH?
THEY'RE DEHYDRATED?
WELL, HOW CAN
SOMETHING HARVESTED
MONTHS AGO BE SEASONAL?
I DON'T MAKE THE RULES,
I JUST PLAY BY THEM.
SOMETHING ELSE YOU WANT?
I HAD MY HEART SET
ON BLUEBERRY PANCAKES.
ARE YOU PREGNANT?I CERTAINLY HOPE SO.
WELL, I'LL HAVE
THE JAYNE MANSFIELD
AND A GRAPEFRUIT JUICE.
JAYNE MANSFIELD?
BLUEBERRY MUFFIN,
BUT JUST THE TOP
OF THE MUFFIN.
SO, BLUEBERRY MUFFINS,
YOU HAVE?
RIGHT, RIGHT, RIGHT.
YOU JUST PLAY BY THEM.
I AM FUCKED.
YOU'RE FUCKED?
MY POST-IT'S AT
AN ICE-SKATING RINK,
AND ALL I GOT IS THIS JACKET.
REAPING 101, LEARN TO LAYER.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT
THE DAY MIGHT BRING.
MAYBE YOU COULD PRAY HER UP
A PAIR OF MITTENS
AND A CUTE SCARF.
WELL, THAT'S NOT WHAT
PRAYER IS FOR, ROXY.
IT'S NOT FOR MAKING
YOURSELF FEEL BETTER
AFTER YOU FUCK UP.
THAT'S WHAT I USE IT FOR.
WHAT'S GOING ON
BETWEEN YOU TWO?
ASK THE NICE
LITTLE CATHOLIC GIRL
WHO LIKES TO STEAL
JEWELRY FROM THE DEAD.
HEY, I NEEDED THIS.
BESIDES, SHE WAS MEAN.
WELL, THE MEAN
WOMAN'S FAMILY THINKS
THE COPS STOLE IT
OFF HER FAT, DEAD NECK
AT THE CRIME SCENE
AND THEY WANT IT BACK.
MAKE HER GIVE IT BACK, RUBE.
NO WAY.NO. YOU KNOW WHAT, LADIES?
I'M HAVING ENOUGH TROUBLE
WITH MY BREAKFAST
THIS MORNING.
GOOD LORD, I BESEECH THEE,
TWO SCRAMBLED EGGS
AND A SMALL OJ, AMEN.
WHY DO YOU PERSECUTE ME?
[KIFFANY] ONE JAYNE MANSFIELD.
MADE YOUR DECISION?
I NEVER THOUGHT
THE DAY WOULD COME,
BUT I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT I WANT TO EAT.
GO WITH BACON.
YOU NEVER REGRET BACON.
OH, IT DOESN'T
FEEL LIKE A BACON DAY.
WHEN'D YOU RUN
OUT OF BLUEBERRIES?
TEN MINUTES AGO.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT YOU WANT?
BETTER TIMING.
SALT.
[HENSON] MOVE THAT PUCK!
GO!
NICE SHOT, ANDY.
YOU SUCK!
MY MOTHER HAS
A BETTER SLAP SHOT
AND SHE'S DEAD.
YOU SEE THESE
LITTLE GIRLS OVER HERE?
I'D RATHER HAVE ONE OF THEM
ON MY POWER PLAY
TOMORROW NIGHT.
[BRIAN] HEY, COACH HENSON!
[ZAMBONI HORN HONKING]
[GEORGE]
MAMA, I'M COMING HOME.
GIVE ME TWO MINUTES, BRIAN.
CAN'T DO IT, COACH.
TIME'S UP.
[GEORGE]  TIME'S UP. GOT TO GO.
ALL RIGHT, GET OUT OF HERE.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE
ANY OF YOU EVER AGAIN.
EXCEPT YOU, ANDY.
GET OVER HERE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OUT HERE?
I'M PLAYING HOCKEY.
HEY, HOW YOU DOING?
FINE.
YOU WANT TO PLAY HOCKEY
OR YOU WANT TO
TALK TO PRETTY GIRLS?
BOTH.
YOU'RE PISSING IT AWAY, ANDY.
YOU GOT IT AND
YOU'RE PISSING IT AWAY.
SORRY, COACH.
YOU CAN GO BACK TO YOUR RANT.
ANY OF YOU GIRLS PLAY HOCKEY?
[GIRLS] I DO!YOU.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?MELISSA.
YOU THINK YOU CAN HANDLE
A HOCKEY STICK
BETTER THAN HIM?
NO, BUT I BET I CAN
PLAY BETTER THAN YOU.
[GIRLS GIGGLING]
PASS ME THE PUCK
WHEN I TELL YOU TO.
NOW.
COACH, WATCH OUT!
OH, MY GOD!
[GEORGE]  HE SHOOTS,
HE DOES NOT SCORE.
AM I DEAD?
AS DEAD AS I'VE
SEEN IN A WHILE.
ARE YOU DEAD?
I WAS KILLED
ABOUT A YEAR AGO,
SO I'M DEAD-ISH.
WHY WAS I KILLED?
[GEORGE] I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T MAKE THE RULES,
I JUST PLAY BY THEM.
CHALK IT UP TO BAD TIMING,
COACH. COME ON.
[GEORGE]  LIFE AND DEATH
WAS KIND OF A GAME,
KIND OF LIKE DUCK DUCK GOOSE.
DUCK, DUCK, DEAD.
WE'RE ALL JUST A STEP AWAY
FROM THAT DREADED
TAP ON THE HEAD.
WE'RE ALL JUST
TRYING NOT TO GET CAUGHT.
AM I INTERRUPTING SOMETHING?
NO, I WAS
JUST WORKING ON...
FIVESIES?FOURSIES.
MILLIE, MILLIE, MILLIE.
HAVE YOU FINISHED
ANYTHING THIS MORNING?
ACTUALLY, I DID
FINISH SOMETHING.
[GEORGE]  SOMEONE.
BIG ASSIGNMENT, MILLIE.
WE'VE GOT A NEW
PHARMACEUTICALS ACCOUNT.
THEY'RE ABOUT A WEEK
FROM A MAJOR DRUG LAUNCH.
THEY'RE TERRIBLY IN NEED
OF A TOP-NOTCH STAFFER.
GOT THAT?
[GEORGE]  BLAH-BLAH, TYPE MEMO,
GO GET A MOCHA, SEND MEMO.
GOT IT.
THESE ARE THE
THREE APPLICANTS YOU
HAVE TO CHOOSE FROM.
BACK UP. DID YOU
JUST SAY CHOOSE? ME?
NO, I SAID YOU CHOOSE.
YOU'RE IN A NEW POSITION NOW.
YOU'RE LIKE THE PRETTIEST
GIRL AT THE PROM,
OR THE SLUTTIEST GIRL
IF YOU WENT TO
CATHOLIC SCHOOL.
YOU GET TO PICK.
WHAT IF I'M NEITHER?
DECISIONS MUST BE MADE.
WINNERS
MAKE DECISIONS, MILLIE.
[GEORGE]
WINNERS MAKE DECISIONS,
BUT NOTHING BEFORE MY MOCHA,
BREAKFAST OF CHAMPIONS.
WE JUST SOLD YOUR HOUSE.
CONGRATULATIONS, YOU TWO.
WELL, WHAT DO
YOU THINK, REGGIE?
I THINK HIGH-FIVES
ARE IN ORDER.
I DON'T THINK SO.
OKAY, THEN.
SO HOW MUCH DID WE MAKE?
A LOT.
HOW MUCH DID SHE MAKE?
SHE DID WELL.DO YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT
MY COMMISSION IS, REGGIE?
GO AHEAD.
I MAKE FIVE PERCENT
OF THE SELLING PRICE.
WHAT A SCAM.
I WANT YOUR JOB
WHEN I GROW UP.
[JOY] NO, YOU DON'T.
[REGGIE] SO ARE WE RICH?
I USUALLY SUGGEST HOLDING OFF
ON THE CELEBRATION
UNTIL CLOSING ESCROW.
WHAT'S ESCROW?
WELL, IT'S A KIND
OF IN-BETWEEN TIME.
IT'S LIKE...
PURGATORY? LIMBO?
SHE'S A READER.
IT'S LIKE BRINGING
A SACK LUNCH TO SCHOOL.
YOUR LUNCH IS IN THE BAG,
BUT YOU HAVE TO WAIT
UNTIL THE BELL RINGS
TO EAT IT.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU JUST
GO AHEAD AND GIVE ME
THAT PAPERWORK, JOY,
I CAN SKEDADDLE.
WHERE ARE WE GONNA LIVE?
WELL, ESCROW
LASTS FOR 45 DAYS,
SO WE HAVE
A MONTH AND A HALF
TO FIND A PLACE.
WAIT. WAIT.
HEY, MAN, WHAT'S THE DEAL?
WHAT THE FUCK, HAVE YOU GOT
A POST-IT HERE, TOO, OR WHAT?
POST-IT? WHAT...WHAT IS THIS?
[MASON] "707 HANLEY BOULEVARD.
707 HANLEY..."
"USED RECORDS CHEAP"?
MAN, THAT SHIT
AIN'T EVEN WORTH IT
UNLESS YOU'RE
INTO THAT VINTAGE
'60S BRITISH THING.
WAIT. I AM VINTAGE
'60S BRITISH THING,
SO FUCK OFF. GO ON.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO]
ANYONE HOME?
SO, MICHAEL,
I SEE FROM YOUR RESUME
THAT YOU ARE
A MAJOR IN CHEMISTRY.
YES, SO IF THERE'S
ANY TECHNICAL STUFF
THAT COMES UP, I'M YOUR MAN.
THIS IS A HIGHLY-PRESSURED
SITUATION, MICHAEL.
LUNATECA IS
LOOKING FOR A SELF...
[FARTING]
...STARTER WITH GREAT
INTERPERSONAL SKILLS.
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
THAT PERSON, MICHAEL?
I KNOW I'M THAT
PERSON, MILLIE.
[FARTING]
LUNATECA IS BRINGING
A NEW PAINKILLER
TO THE MARKET
WITHIN THE NEXT FEW DAYS
AND THEY'RE
HOPING TO HIRE SOMEONE
BEFORE THE DRUG IS...
[FARTING]
RELEASED.
MICHAEL, YOU ARE FARTING.I'M AWARE OF THAT.
YOU DO REALIZE
THIS ISN'T A JOB
AT A MORNING RADIO SHOW?
[FARTING]
I'LL TAKE THAT AS A NO.
LISTEN, I HAVE
IRRITABLE BOWEL SYNDROME,
OKAY?
IT'S NOT A JOKE.
IN FACT, IT'S PROTECTED
BY THE AMERICANS
WITH DISABILITIES ACT
SO DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT TRYING TO GET
RID OF ME FOR THIS.
[FARTING]
I APPRECIATE YOU COMING IN.
LEAVE THE DOOR OPEN?PLEASE.
YEAH, THEY'RE ALL FOR SALE.
ANYTHING YOU SEE.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO]
YOU BREAK IT, YOU BUY IT.
HOW MUCH FOR
THAT ONE, MATE?NOT THAT ONE.
ANYTHING ELSE.
HOW ABOUT THIS ONE?YEAH, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
ANYTHING BUT THAT ONE.
ARE YOU SELLING
YOUR RECORDS OR WHAT?
WELL, I'M ALWAYS
A BIT CLEARER AFTER LUNCH.
"THE CHURCH YARD
AT WEMBLEY, 1965."
FUCKING HELL.
HANG ON, THEY DID
NOT DO LIVE RECORDINGS
OF THIS SHOW, MATE.
BAND MADE THEIR OWN.
YEAH.
YOU KNEW SOMEBODY
IN THE CHURCH YARD?
FUCK OFF.
DID YOU?
ALL MY LIFE.
BLOODY HELL.
BLOODY HELL,
YOU'RE GIDEON JEFFRIES.
DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE
ANOTHER LONG-LOST CHILD
OF SOME GROUPIE
BECAUSE I'M TAPPED OUT.
WHY DON'T YOU TRY JAGGER?
HE'S STILL TOURING.
SORRY.
LOOK, I'M JUST
SUCH A TREMENDOUS,
BLOODY FAN OF YOURS, MAN.
I MEAN, THIS WASN'T
EVEN A CONCERT, WAS IT?
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
IT WAS A FUCKING MIRACLE.
THAT CONCERT
WAS 40 YEARS AGO.
YOU'VE GOT TO BE THINKING
ABOUT SOMETHING ELSE, MATE.
YEAH, MY UNCLE USED
TO REMINISCE ABOUT IT
ALL THE TIME.
DIDN'T SHUT UP
ABOUT IT. YEAH.YOUR UNCLE?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[MAN] CHINESE FOOD.BRILLIANT.
LISTEN, DO YOU HAVE,
LIKE, 20 BUCKS ON YOU?
I'VE GOT 20 BUCKS ON ME.
IT'S A BIT EARLY FOR CHINESE,
BUT ANYTHING FOR YOU,
GIDEON JEFFRIES.
FUCK, GIDEON JEFFRIES.
THAT'S A PARKING TICKET.
THAT'S A PARKING TICKET, YEAH,
AND YOU KNOW WHAT'S
FUCKED UP ABOUT IT?
I DON'T EVEN
FUCKING HAVE A CAR.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I'VE
GOT A PARKING TICKET
IN MY...
DO YOU HAVE A 20 ON YOU?
I'VE GOT A FUCKING...
I'VE GOT A 20, MATE.
I'VE GOT A...
FUCK, WHAT THE FUCK?
THERE IT IS. THERE'S A 20.
ALL RIGHT, CHEERS.
TAKE A RECORD,
JUST NOT THAT ONE, OKAY?
GIDEON JEFFRIES, FUCK.
EGG ROLLS, FRIEND.
HEY, YOU LIKE CHINESE?
YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU LIKE CHINESE.
TAKE A CARD.
IT'S OKAY.
HERE YOU GO.THANKS.
OFFER YOU A BITE?
I'M TRYING TO CUT BACK, MATE.
ALL THAT MSG. TOXIC.
REALLY BAD FOR YOU.
WHAT DID YOU
SAY YOUR NAME WAS?
MASON.
I USED TO BE GIDEON JEFFRIES.
I REMEMBER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU
SOLD OUR LILY PAD.
EXCUSE ME?
MRS. RODRIGUEZ SAID
THAT FROGS LIKE TO
STAY ON ONE LILY PAD
UNTIL ANOTHER
LILY PAD DRIFTS BY.
SHE SAID THEY DON'T
REALLY LIKE TO SWIM.
THAT'S WHERE
THE DANGER IS, THE POND.
BUT WHAT IS YOUR POINT?
RIBBIT. WE'RE IN THE POND.
WE ARE NOT IN THE POND.
EXCUSE US.
[DOOR BUZZING]
WHAT IS THAT?
SOME PEOPLE DOWNTOWN
LIVE IN PLACES LIKE THAT.
WHAT KIND OF PEOPLE?
DOWNTOWN PEOPLE.
YOU KNOW,
HOW ABOUT JUST FOR FUN
WE GO LOOK AT A LILY PAD?
YOU GET ME JOB.
USUALLY WE WARM UP
WITH A LITTLE SMALL TALK
BEFORE THE COMMANDS BEGIN.
I'M SORRY.
MY ENGLISH IS NOT PERFECT.
PERHAPS OTHERS
ARE MORE POLITE.
YOU'D BE SURPRISED.
I DIDN'T DO IT.
IT WAS THE GUY BEFORE YOU.
ANYWAY, YOU'RE RUSSIAN?
CHECHNYA. BIG DIFFERENCE.
YOU KNOW WHERE
THIS IS, CHECHNYA?
NOT REALLY.
THIS JOB, ANTON,
IS NOT ENTRY-LEVEL.
IT'S GOING TO BE
VERY STRESSFUL,
A PRESSURE-FILLED SITUATION.
I WAS DOCTOR IN CHECHNYA.
THEN WAR CAME.
MY HOSPITAL WAS BOMBED.
I WAS TORTURED.
ELECTRODES WERE
ATTACHED TO MY TESTICLES.
SO YOU'RE ALL SET ON
THE PRESSURE THING.
I DON'T GET JOB,
LOSE WORK VISA, GO BACK.
YOU GET ME JOB?
MAYBE.
WANT A DONUT?
I NEED JOB, NOT DONUTS.
I GET JOB, BUY DONUTS.
KRISPY KREMES.
THIS IS AWESOME.
YOU CAN SKATEBOARD
IN YOUR OWN LIVING ROOM.
BUT YOU WOULDN'T.
ANYWAY, PEOPLE
THAT WORK DOWNTOWN
LOVE LIVING HERE.
YOU WORK DOWNTOWN?[REGGIE] SHE DOESN'T
WORK ANYWHERE.
SHE'S A MOM.
I USED TO WORK.
WHERE WOULD I SLEEP?
OH, YOUR BEDROOM? THAT WAY.
SO WHERE ARE YOU LIVING NOW?
DO YOU KNOW BEATRICE LANE?
NO, AND BEATRICE LANE
DOES NOT KNOW ME.
[CHUCKLES]
SO IS IT...
IS IT SAFE DOWN HERE?
WELL, DURING THE DAY
EVERYBODY RUSHES AROUND
WITH THEIR WORK
AND DURING THE NIGHT,
EVERYBODY RUSHES
AROUND WITH THEIR PLAY.
SO YOU CAN BE BY YOURSELF,
BUT YOU'RE NEVER ALONE.
THAT SOUNDS NICE.
YEAH.
IS IT JUST THE TWO OF YOU?YEP.
THAT'S WHAT IT IS. YEAH.
MY ROOM'S HUGE.
DO YOU ALLOW DOGS?
YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED
TO MOVE IN WITHOUT ONE.
COOL.
I GUESS SHE LIKES IT.
SEEMS THAT WAY.
AND SHE DOESN'T
LIKE ANYTHING.
SO DID YOU SELL YOUR PLACE
ON BEATRICE LANE?
I'M IN ESCROW.
YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU NEED TO DO?
YOU NEED TO CRUISE BY,
CHECK OUT THE NEIGHBORHOOD
AT NIGHT, SEE IF YOU LIKE IT.
YOUR ROOM HAS
A FIREPLACE IN IT
AND A VIEW OF THE SOUND.
HEY, WHAT'S THE
NAME OF YOUR DOG?J.D.
J.D. WHAT'S J.D. STAND FOR?
JUST DOG.
JUST... OF COURSE.
I LIKE GOLDEN RETRIEVERS.
SO WHAT DID HER FAMILY SAY?
YOU MEAN, THE GRIEVING,
STOLEN-CROSS FAMILY?
YEAH.THEY CAME TO THE PRECINCT
AND COMPLAINED.
THEY THINK THE COPS STOLE IT.
IT'S AN HEIRLOOM OR SOME SHIT.
THE FUCKING THING IS
OLDER THAN YOU ARE.
THERE'S NO NEED TO BE MEAN.
JUST GIVE IT BACK.THERE'S NO LAW
THAT SAYS I HAVE TO.
ACTUALLY, THERE
ARE SEVERAL LAWS,
DAISY ADAIR,
INCLUDING YOU-KNOW-WHO'S.
NO NEED TO BRING HIM INTO IT.
I'M KEEPING THE CROSS.
I WILL SAY ONE THING.
YOU GOT GOOD TASTE.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL CROSS.THANK YOU.
THE THING IS GOING
TO BURN A HOLE CLEAN
THROUGH YOUR NECK
TO THE BACK OF YOUR SPINE.
SO HE WAS...
BREAKING WIND
THROUGH THE WHOLE INTERVIEW?
JUST RIPPING
ONE AFTER ANOTHER.
THAT'S FUNNY, CRYSTAL?
NO.
IT IS A LITTLE FUNNY.
MILLIE.I'M SORRY.
IRRITABLE BOWEL SYNDROME
IS A SERIOUS AFFLICTION.
MOST PEOPLE DON'T KNOW THIS,
BUT MARILYN MONROE HAD IBS.
IS THAT WHAT
BLEW HER SKIRT UP?
THAT IS IN
POOR TASTE, MILLIE.
I'M SORRY AGAIN.
KNOCK, KNOCK.
I HAVE AN APPOINTMENT
WITH MILLIE.
MARGARET PADDINGTON?
AS IN THE BEAR?
AS IN THE BEAR.
HI. I'M MILLIE.
THANKS FOR COMING IN.
I CAN'T TELL YOU
HOW MUCH THIS
INTERVIEW MEANS TO ME.
AT MY AGE,
I'M LUCKY TO EVEN
GET A CALL RETURNED.
OH, DON'T BE SILLY.
WE'RE HAPPY TO HAVE YOU.
I GUESS IT'S
TRUE WHAT THEY SAY
ABOUT THE MAGICAL SUPERPOWERS
A WOMAN GETS
WHEN SHE TURNS 50.
WHAT'S THAT?
SHE CAN DISAPPEAR.
I TOOK 10 YEARS OFF
TO CARE FOR MY AGING PARENTS
WHO HAVE NOW PASSED.
OH, I'M SORRY.
WELL, I SHOULD NEVER
HAVE LEFT THE WORKFORCE.
IT'S SO HARD NOW
TO GET BACK IN.
I SHOULD NEVER HAVE
JUMPED OFF THAT TRAIN
AND NOW I'VE LIVED
WITH DEATH FOR SO LONG
THAT, WELL,
I NEED TO FEEL ALIVE.
[CLEARS THROAT]
LET'S SEE WHAT
WE CAN DO FOR YOU.
[MASON] GIDEON.
GIDEON JEFFRIES.
I JUST WANT TO TELL YOU
HOW GREAT YOU ARE, MAN.
I MEAN, YOU INVENTED
THE POWER STANCE.
NOW, YOU...
DO YOU MIND IF I JUST...
[YELLING]
THANK YOU, BATON ROUGE.
DO YOU MIND IF YOU
DO IT FOR ME? PLEASE.
NO.
POWER STANCE
DAYS ARE BEHIND ME.
RIGHT, YEAH, I'M SORRY.
IT'S STUPID. I'M SORRY
FOR ASKING, MAN.
NO, NO, DON'T BE SORRY.
IT'S NOT STUPID.
SEE, THE WHO
STARTED ALL THIS NONSENSE.
TOWNSHEND. IT WAS JUST
ANOTHER ROCK-STAR
AFFECTATION, YOU KNOW.
IT DIDN'T ACTUALLY PRODUCE
MORE SOUND THAT WAY.
BUT IT WAS SO
FUCKING COOL, WASN'T IT?
WELL, EVERYTHING LOOKS
COOL WHEN YOU'RE 27.
WHAT THE FUCK DO YOU KNOW?
YOU'RE STILL A KID.
DO YOU MIND IF I
EAT MY CHINESE NOW?
CAN I JUST ASK
YOU ONE QUESTION
BEFORE YOU...
BEFORE WHAT?NOTHING.
ANYWAY, MY UNCLE,
I SWEAR TO GOD,
HE WORSHIPPED YOU, MAN.
YOU KNOW, AND HE ENDED UP
CHASING THIS PERMANENT HIGH.
ANYWAY, HE THOUGHT
THAT IF HE'S GOING TO GO OUT,
HE'S GOING TO GO
OUT LIKE HIS HEROES.
YOU KNOW, HE'S GOING
TO GO OUT LIKE THOSE,
LIKE THOSE BLOKES
FROM THE CHURCH YARD.
HOW DID IT TURN
OUT FOR YOUR UNCLE?
NOT TOO WELL.
HE ENDED UP IN A CHURCHYARD.
WELL, DOESN'T IT ALWAYS?
WHAT?DID YOU EVER GET THERE?
THE ULTIMATE HIGH?
I'M STILL WAITING.
GOOD LUCK.
[GEORGE]
"EENIE, MEENIE, MINIE, MOE,
CATCH A TIGER BY ITS TOE,
"IF HE HOLLERS, LET HIM GO."
MY BOSS SAID TO
PICK THE VERY BEST ONE,
BUT WHO THE FUCK IS THAT?
OKAY. WHAT THE HELL?
FROM THE CHECHNYAN?
SMELLS LIKE IT'S
FROM THE OTHER GUY.
GIFTS FROM AN APPLICANT?
THE NO-NO OF NO-NOS.
I KNOW.
I'M COUNTING ON YOU, MILLIE.
I HOPE YOU'RE AT
LEAST NARROWING IT DOWN.
ABSOLUTELY.
[GEORGE]  ROCK, PAPER,
SCISSORS, MATCH.
FUCK.
OKAY, WHAT WAS THE BEST THING
ABOUT BEING A ROCK STAR?
THE SAME THING
AS THE WORST, ALL THE GIRLS.
SHUT THE FUCK UP.
HOW WAS THAT
POSSIBLY THE WORST?
I HAD A FAMILY
AND THEY LEFT ME.
MY WIFE GOT SICK
OF MY REPEATED INDISCRETIONS.
I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
I MEAN, SHE MARRIED
A ROCK STAR.
WHAT DID SHE EXPECT?
I ALWAYS BLAMED THE DRUGS.
THEY MADE ME FEEL
DEFIANT,
FEARLESS, IMMORTAL.
YOU ARE IMMORTAL.
YOU MADE MUSIC.
YOU LIVE FOREVER.
I BEG TO DIFFER.
SO EMBARRASSING,
BUT I WANTED TO
BE YOU SO BADLY.
I WAS...
I WAS THERE.
THE CHURCH YARD LIVE,
1965, AT WEMBLEY.
HOW OLD ARE YOU?
I'M THE SAME AGE
AS I WAS THEN.
I'M BEGINNING TO GET THIS.
YOU'VE JUST BEEN
HANGING AROUND FOR YEARS
LURKING IN THE CORNER.
YEAH. IMMORTAL.
IT'S NOT ALL IT'S
CRACKED UP TO BE.
THAT'S GOOD TO KNOW.
SO DO YOU MIND IF
I KEEP THIS ONE?
NO, I DON'T MIND.
TAKE ANYTHING YOU LIKE.
JUST DO ME ONE GOOD TURN.
ANYTHING, MAN.
TAKE THE NEEDLE OUT
BEFORE THE POLICE ARRIVE.
I DON'T WANT THEM
TAKING PICTURES OF THAT.
MY KIDS MIGHT SEE IT.
I'M NOT MEANT TO
FUCK AROUND WITH ANYTHING,
BUT FOR THE MAN WHO INVENTED
THE POWER STANCE, OF COURSE.
YOU MEAN, LIKE THIS?
[GUITAR CHORD PLAYING]
[LAUGHS]
NICE.
FORGIVE ME,
FATHER, FOR I HAVE SINNED.
IT'S BEEN 75 YEARS
SINCE MY LAST CONFESSION.
HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
IT FEELS LIKE 75 YEARS.
WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE
TO CONFESS, MY CHILD?
PETTY LARCENY,
AND FROM A VERY
UNPLEASANT WOMAN.
SO HOW MANY HAIL MARYS
AND OUR FATHERS IS THAT?
WHAT DID YOU TAKE?
A NECKLACE
WITH A CROSS ON IT.
I NEEDED IT.
AND THIS PERSON YOU TOOK
THE CROSS FROM DID NOT?
NO.
WHY NOT?
SHE WAS DEAD.
THAT IS WHEN WE
NEED IT THE MOST.
HOW ABOUT WE
SAY 10 HAIL MARYS
AND FOUR OUR FATHERS,
AND WE'LL CALL IT ABSOLVED?
WOULDN'T YOU RATHER TALK
ABOUT WHY YOU FELT THE NEED
TO STEAL A CROSS
FROM A DEAD WOMAN?
NO, I THINK THE ACT
SPEAKS FOR ITSELF.
SO HOW ABOUT MY PENANCE?
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
DAISY. DAISY ADAIR.
NOW, HOW ABOUT THAT PENANCE?
I CAN SAY THE WORDS,
BUT IT MIGHT BE
BETTER IF YOU TELL ME
WHAT'S REALLY ON YOUR MIND.
I'M WAITING FOR SOMETHING.
I DON'T KNOW.
THE CROSS MAKES ME
FEEL CLOSER TO IT.
WELL, WHETHER WE'RE
WAITING FOR SOMEONE
TO SAY THEY LOVE US,
WAITING FOR A CHECK TO CLEAR,
WAITING FOR
A MAN OF THE CLOTH
TO SAY WE'RE FORGIVEN,
GRACE IS PASSING
BY US EVERY DAY
AND WE KNOW NOT WHEN
THE END OF OUR DAYS
MAY BE UPON US.
I KNOW ALL
ABOUT THAT, FATHER.
I JUST WANT
MY PENANCE, PLEASE.
BLESS YOU, MY CHILD.
TWO HAIL MARYS AND
AN ACT OF CONTRITION.
I HAVE TO GO.
[GEORGE]  I WAS FINDING
THAT THE BEST WAY
TO AVOID TAKING RESPONSIBILITY
WAS TO AVOID THE PERSON
WHO GAVE YOU
THE RESPONSIBILITY.
I'M SO FUCKING SMART,
I SCARE MYSELF.
[EXCLAIMS]
HOW DID YOU DO THAT?
DO YOU HAVE TIME
TO HEAR A MESSAGE
ON MY VOICE MAIL?
[CAT MEOWING]
OH, THAT'S JUST MURRAY.
HE LEARNED SPEED DIAL.
SUCH A GOOD BOY.
HOW IS MURRAY?
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT
CHANGING THE SUBJECT.
HE'S OKAY.
[BEEPING]
DELORES, THIS IS NED.
WHERE'S MY
FUCKING TEMP, DELORES?
I'M SITTING ON
A SHIT VOLCANO HERE!
I'M ON TOP OF MOUNT
SAINT SHIT, DELORES!
HELP ME!
THAT IS NED BENJAMIN
FROM LUNATECA.
HE'S YOUR CLIENT.
YOUR CLIENT IS NOT HAPPY.
I'M WORKING ON IT. I SWEAR.
[PHONE RINGING]
[DELORES] WHAT IS IT, CRYSTAL?
PACKAGE FOR MILLIE.
IT'S MOVING.
WHY IS IT MOVING?
IT'S ALIVE.
OH.
OH, GOD.
YOU HAVE TO MAKE
THE DECISION, MILLIE.
DON'T LET
THE DECISION MAKE YOU.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS.
PICK SOMEONE.
LOSE THE RABBIT.
HI, MILLIE.
HI, MICHAEL.
HI. I WAS JUST
HOPING WE COULD REVISIT
FOR A MOMENT
TODAY'S INTERVIEW.
[GEORGE]  OH, PLEASE, GOD,
I CAN'T TAKE ANOTHER BLAST.
YOU WERE GREAT, MICHAEL.
YOU'RE DEFINITELY
STILL IN THE MIX.
COOL. I JUST WANTED
TO LET YOU KNOW
I'M NOT GOING
TO SUE HAPPY TIME
IF YOU DON'T CHOOSE ME.
I'M DONE BLAMING
OTHERS FOR MY PROBLEM.
WELL, THAT'S VERY
MATURE OF YOU TO SAY.
SO ARE YOU GOING
TO CHOOSE ME?
I DON'T KNOW. MAYBE.
WELL, IF IT HELPS,
I THINK YOU SHOULD KNOW
THAT I STARTED
NEW MEDICATION TODAY
AND IT'S BEEN
INCREDIBLY EFFECTIVE.
WELL, GOOD FOR YOU.
[FARTS]
WOW, DID YOU HEAR
THE RABBIT FART?
WHEN'S DINNER?
WHENEVER YOU WANT.
YOU'RE HAVING
A BABYSITTER TONIGHT, OKAY?
TILL HOW LATE?
WELL, NOT LATE ENOUGH
FOR YOU TO WATCH  LETTERMAN,
IF THAT'S WHAT
YOU'RE GETTING AT.
I DON'T WANT TO
WATCH  LETTERMAN.
YOU CAN ORDER PIZZA.
DO YOU HAVE A DATE?
NO, I HAVE AN APPOINTMENT.
DO I LOOK LIKE I HAVE A DATE?
NO.
DO I LOOK BAD?
NO. CAN I HAVE PEPPERONI?
NO.
I'M LEAVING, MILLIE.
I'M LEAVING WITHOUT
GIVING NED BENJAMIN
YOUR DECISION.
I JUST HAVE
TO SLEEP ON IT.
THEY NEEDED SOMEONE TODAY.
IT WILL ALL BE
CLEARER IN THE MORNING.
OKAY, MILLIE, YOU'RE
IN CHARGE. I'M LEAVING.
I'VE GOT MY SHOWS TO WATCH.
[GEORGE]  I DIDN'T
WANT TO BE IN CHARGE.
I WANTED TO GO HOME
AND STARE AT MY TV.
BEING IN CHARGE
WAS THE LONELIEST
FEELING EVER.
ALL RIGHT,
THE SECOND LONELIEST.
I'M NOT GOING HOME.
I'D JUST CHANNEL-SURF
ALL NIGHT ANYWAY.
CAN'T MAKE A DECISION
ABOUT ANYTHING.
WE HAVE CABLE.
EVERYBODY HAS CABLE.
WE HAVE PAY STATIONS,
YOU KNOW, WITH SWEARING.
WOW, SWEARING.
PRETTY TOUGH, HUH?
MY SISTER DIED.
HOW DID SHE DIE?
SKYDIVING.
MY MOM SAID WE
COULD ORDER PIZZA.
PEPPERONI.
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
[BANGING ON DOOR]
[J.D. BARKING]
SHIT.
CAN YOU WAIT
HERE FOR A SECOND?
I LIVE HERE, SO YEAH.
[JANELLE]
WHAT THE FUCK, MICAH?
[MICAH] TOMMY SAID NOW.
THEY'RE DOING IT NOW.
[JANELLE]
I AM GOING TO BEAT HIS ASS,
I SWEAR TO FUCKING GOD.
[DOOR SLAMMING]
HI. I'VE GOT TO GO
FOR ABOUT AN HOUR.
YOU'RE COOL, RIGHT?
I'M COOL.
DON'T TELL YOUR MOM.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[BRAZILIAN MUSIC PLAYING]
THIS TIME OF YEAR,
YOU COULD SEE
SATURN'S RINGS
WITH THE NAKED EYE
IF YOU'VE HAD
ENOUGH TO DRINK.
[LAUGHS]
WHERE'S THE MUSIC
COMING FROM?
NOW, THAT'S THE
BRAZILIAN CLUB ON FOURTH,
AND IN THE SUMMERTIME
YOU CAN SEE CHAMBER MUSIC
ON THAT ROOFTOP.
YOU PLAY MUSIC?
PIANO. WHEN I WAS A KID.
YOU PAINT? I PAINT.
ARE YOU A WRITER?
NO.
YOU SEEM LIKE YOU COULD.
LIKE YOU HAVE STORIES TO TELL.
MAYBE.
YOU LIKE THE PLACE,
THOUGH, RIGHT?
I DO, BUT WE'RE...
I'M IN ESCROW.
SO, YOU KNOW,
IT'S NOT A GOOD
TIME TO WANT ANYTHING.
WELL, DO YOU WANT
A GLASS OF WINE?
[THUDDING]
HELLO?
[RATTLING]
GEORGE? IS THAT YOU?
YOU HAVE
VERY PRETTY FEATURES,
VERY PRETTY AND VERY SAD.
I NEED TO GET
HOME TO MY DAUGHTER.
SHE HAS A BABYSITTER.
SHE'S SAFE.
WHY YOU WORRY SO MUCH?
YEAH, WHY WORRY, RIGHT?
TWO GREAT GIRLS,
HOUSE IN A NICE NEIGHBORHOOD,
THE TEACHER,
YOU MAKE ALL
THE RIGHT CHOICES
AND THINGS FALL APART.
"I MADE ME GREAT WORKS,
"I BUILDED ME HOUSES,
I PLANTED ME VINEYARDS.
"AND, BEHOLD, ALL WAS VANITY
AND VEXATION OF SPIRIT."
ECCLESIASTES.
RIGHT.
THAT'S THE ONE
PART OF THE BIBLE
I REMEMBER.
IT WAS ALL ABOUT LISTS.
I FIND LISTS VERY COMFORTING.
A TIME TO LIVE,
A TIME TO DIE.
THERE IT IS.
THERE'S THAT SADNESS.
[SIGHING]
I WANT THIS APARTMENT.
I WANT THIS LIFE.
LET ME DO ONE MORE.
JUST ONE MORE.
FINE, ONE MORE.
DRAW ME HAPPY.
GEORGE?
[THUNDER CRASHING]
I'M MAKING EVERYONE UNHAPPY.
EVERYONE HATES ME,
ALL OF THESE PEOPLE.
PHARMACEUTICAL NED,
YOU SHOULD'VE HEARD HIM
ON THE PHONE TODAY.
HE REALLY HATES ME.
WHY ON EARTH IS
THIS SO HARD FOR YOU?
BECAUSE THEY ALL WANT IT
AND THEY ALL CAN HANDLE IT,
BUT WHO TO CHOOSE?
HOW TO CHOOSE?
YOU SOUND LIKE HAMLET.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
I SOUND LIKE HAMLET?
ALL THAT INDECISION.
I WAS OPHELIA
IN PROVINCETOWN.
SEEMS APPROPRIATE.
OPHELIA WAS THE ONE
WHO DROWNED, RIGHT?
YEAH. SIX NIGHTS A WEEK
AND TWICE ON SUNDAY.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
THAT'S MASON'S KNOCK.
ALLOW ME.
[MASON] HEY. RUBE CALLED.
GROUP REAP TOMORROW.
DRESS CODE IS BUSINESS CASUAL.
[GEORGE] YOU COULDN'T
HAVE CALLED?
OH, I WANTED TO
PLAY A RECORD.
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOUR STEREO?
WELL, THE CRACKHEAD
I SOLD IT TO HAS IT.
[SCRATCHY ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
WHAT IS THAT DREADFUL NOISE?
IT'S A MEMORY
OF SOMETHING THAT DOESN'T
QUITE MATCH A MEMORY.
ARE YOU DRINKING TONIGHT?SOBER AS A PRIEST.
YOU KNOW, GEORGIA,
IF YOU CAN'T DECIDE,
GIVE IT UP TO GOD.
LET HIM DECIDE.
I WOULDN'T LET
GOD DECIDE, GEORGE.
WHY?
LOOK HOW HE FUCKED US.
[JOY] OH, MY GOD.
REGGIE! REGGIE!
OH, GOD.
WHAT IS IT? WHAT HAPPENED?
REGGIE, ARE YOU OKAY?
I HEARD VOICES UPSTAIRS,
LIKE SOMEONE WAS IN THE HOUSE.
SOMEONE WAS IN THE HOUSE?
EVERYTHING'S FINE, MA'AM.
NO ONE WAS IN THE HOUSE.
I THINK THE LITTLE
GIRL JUST GOT SCARED
BEING ALONE.
YOU TOLD ME,
IN AN EMERGENCY,
TO CALL 911.
WELL, WHERE IS JANELLE?
SHE TOOK OFF HOURS AGO.
I THINK SHE'S
A DEVIL WORSHIPER.
SHE'S GOING TO
STANFORD NEXT YEAR.
SHE COULDN'T GET
YOU ON THE CELL PHONE.
WHAT?
OH, IT'S TURNED OFF.
I'M SO SORRY, SWEETIE.
WE WILL NEED TO CONTACT
CHILD PROTECTION SERVICES.
I WILL HANDLE
THE BABYSITTER MYSELF.
ACTUALLY, THEY'LL
BE INTERVIEWING YOU.
EVERY INCIDENT INVOLVING
A MINOR REQUIRES IT.
OH, PLEASE, WHAT ARE YOU...
LOOK AT ME.
DO I LOOK LIKE SOMEBODY
WHO WOULD ENDANGER A CHILD?
HAVE YOU HAD
ANYTHING TO DRINK
THIS EVENING, MA'AM?
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
YEAH.
WELL, OKAY,
SO THANK YOU, OFFICERS,
SO MUCH FOR RESPONDING.
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
GOOD NIGHT.
YOU HAVE A GOOD NIGHT, TOO.
WHERE WERE YOU?
I WENT TO LOOK
AT THAT APARTMENT.
IT GOT LATE.
I'M SORRY.
LINDA WANTS YOU TO
CALL HER IN THE MORNING.
DID SHE SAY IF IT
WAS ABOUT ESCROW?
SHE JUST SAID TO CALL HER.
ALL RIGHT. WELL,
IT'S TIME FOR BED, SWEETIE.
MOM, I'M NOT TIRED.
YOU WANT TO SLEEP
IN MY ROOM TONIGHT?
MMM-HMM.
WHERE WERE
THE VOICES COMING FROM?
THE ROOF.
WELL, THE BIG TREE
SOUNDS LIKE VOICES
WHEN IT'S WINDY.
[GEORGE]  SOMETIMES,
I CAN'T HEAR MY OWN VOICE.
I WISH I COULD BE LIKE DEATH.
DEATH CHOOSES
WITHOUT BLINKING AN EYE.
DEATH DOESN'T
GATHER INFORMATION.
DEATH DOESN'T ASK QUESTIONS.
IT JUST CHOOSES.
TO JUMP OR NOT TO JUMP?
[RIBBITS]
WE HAVE A WINNER.
HELLO.
[RUBE] YOU CALL THAT
"BUSINESS CASUAL"?YEP.
IF YOU'RE IN
THE DRUG BUSINESS.
I'M NOT IN
WHAT DO YOU
THINK OF MY OUTFIT?
IT'S VERY SMART.
IT'S VERY ROSALIND RUSSELL.
THAT'S A GOOD THING.
CAN I GET A HALF-CAFF
WITH FOAM, CREAM
AND EXTRA SUGAR TO GO?
LET'S GET REAPING.
WHAT HAVE WE GOT, RUBE?
WELL, PEOPLE,
THIS IS A GROUP JOB.
WE'VE GOT ONE ADDRESS,
13 SOULS.
I'VE GOT THREE
APIECE FOR THE LADIES,
I'VE GOT TWO FOR MASON,
TWO FOR ME.
I'VE GOT A PAIR
OF MEN'S SLACKS
IN THE CAR FOR YOU.
I DON'T WEAR SLACKS.YOU WILL THIS MORNING.
YOU, YOU, YOU, YOU.
I DO NOT SMOKE.
YOU WILL THIS MORNING.
IT'S OUR COVER.
WE'RE JUST GOING
TO STAND OUTSIDE
THE BUILDING AND SMOKE.
I WOULD LOVE TO SEE
SOME INHALING, PEOPLE
AND I WOULD LOVE
IF YOU COULD TRY TO
MAKE IT LOOK REAL.
WELL, LET'S GET CRACKING.
WHO WANTS A RIDE?
I WANT A RIDE. SHOTGUN.
RUBE, THESE SLACKS
YOU'VE BROUGHT ME
ARE HORRIBLE, AREN'T THEY?
NO, NO, NO,
THEY'RE NOT HORRIBLE.
AND I ALWAYS RIDE SHOTGUN.
HOW MUCH WILL THAT COST?
OH. OKAY.
WELL, WILL THEY REVISIT IT
IF WE GET THE ROOF FIXED?
OKAY. THANKS, LINDA.
WHAT DID SHE SAY?
IT'S DONE.
WE SOLD THE HOUSE?
WE HAVE TO LEAVE?
WE HAVE TO STAY.
THE DEAL FELL THROUGH.
IT'S THE ROOF.
THERE'S SOME KIND
OF CRACK UP THERE.
A VERY EXPENSIVE CRACK.
I TOLD YOU I HEARD VOICES.
WHO'S GONNA GIVE US THE MONEY
TO FIX IT, REGGIE?
DAD?
HARDLY.
GRANDMA PHYL COULD.
I'M NOT GONNA ASK MY MOTHER.
I MISS HER.
YOU MISS YOUR GRANDMOTHER?
WE SHOULDN'T MOVE.
WE'LL SEE.
IF WE MOVED,
SHE WOULDN'T KNOW
WHERE TO FIND US.
OH.
SEPARATE GROUPS.
LET'S NOT LOOK LIKE
SOME KIND OF LINEUP.
KEEP YOUR COVER.
PARDON ME, HANDSOME.
DO YOU HAVE A LIGHT?
I'LL GET YOU ONE.THANKS.
[GEORGE]  TIMING,
DAISY HAD IT IN SPADES.
SHE DIDN'T STOP TO WONDER
WHY ONE GUY GOT IT
AND NOT ANOTHER.
IT WAS HIS TIME.
THAT'S ALL.
IT IS ME, ANTON PLOTNICK.
YOU'RE HERE TO GREET ME.I AM?
[ANTON] IN MY CULTURE,
A MAN DOES NOT EASILY
EXPRESS HIS FEELINGS,
BUT I AM GRATEFUL
TO START NEW LIFE.
THANK YOU.
TIME FOR WORK. GOODBYE.
ARE YOU OKAY, GEORGE?
NO.
[NED] SHIT VOLCANO.
THAT'S ALL IT IS.
I'M JUST ON TOP OF A SHIT...
I THINK WE HAVE OUR SHOOTER.
[NED] I'M JUST ON
TOP OF A SHIT VOLCANO.
NED BENJAMIN?
WHAT'S IT TO YOU?NOTHING.
[NED] DON'T TOUCH MY BAG!
ROXY NAILED IT, RAMPAGE.
WHAT CAN I SAY?
WHAT'S WRONG, GEORGE?
I'M GOOD.
[GUN FIRING]
THAT WAS HORRIBLE.
NOW?
[GUN FIRES]
THAT WAS NED BENJAMIN.
[GEORGE]  I ACTUALLY READ
HAMLET  IN HIGH SCHOOL.
THE GUY CAN'T MAKE A DECISION,
AND EVERYBODY DIES.
I AM HAMLET,
MILLIE, I WANT TO
SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
CAN I PUT MY BAG DOWN FIRST?
I HAD A REALLY ROUGH MORNING.
OH, I THINK YOU'LL
AGREE THIS IS WORTH IT.
WHAT IS IT?
JOB PLACEMENTS,
ALL OVER THE CITY.
JUST LOOK AT ALL THOSE
LOVELY LITTLE STICKPINS.
SEE THE EFFECT WE HAVE?
WE'RE LIKE JOHNNY APPLESEEDS,
PLANTING, THRIVING...
IT'S REALLY COOL, DELORES.
THANK YOU.
DO YOU KNOW,
I HAVE BEEN CALLING
OVER TO LUNATECA
ALL MORNING
AND THERE'S NO ANSWER?
IT'S RUSH, RUSH,
RUSH WHEN THEY NEED YOU,
AND THEN IT'S,
"HAPPY TIME WHO?"
LISTEN, DELORES,
AS MUCH AS I'M FLATTERED
BY THE NEW RESPONSIBILITIES,
I DON'T THINK
I'M UP TO THE TASK
OF PLACING PEOPLE.
NONSENSE, YOU DID FINE.
YOU JUST NEED TO JUMP IN.
I DON'T FEEL
QUALIFIED TO CHOOSE.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
THIS IS DELORES.
OH, MY LORD.
[GEORGE]  TO EVERYTHING
THERE IS A SEASON,
A TIME TO STAY
AND A TIME TO
GET THE HELL OUT.
OH, THOSE POOR PEOPLE.
[GEORGE]  AND FOR NOW,
IT'S STILL HOCKEY SEASON.
SEEMS TO ME YOU CAN EITHER
HAVE SOMEONE TELL YOU
WHAT TO DO WITH YOUR LIFE,
OR YOU CAN LOOK
SOMEWHERE ELSE FOR ANSWERS.
IT'S LIKE YOU
HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
WHERE YOUR GUT IS
AND THEN GO WITH IT.
SURE BEATS STANDING AROUND
THE PUNCH BOWL WITH
THE REST OF THE LOSERS.
HE SHOOTS, HE SCORES.
HEY. I'M GEORGE.
I'M ANDY.
[GEORGE]  SEEMS TO ME,
EITHER YOU SHOW UP
AT THE DANCE OR
YOU JUST STAY HOME.
ONE, TWO, THREE,
ONE, TWO, THREE.