[GEORGE]:  WHEN I WAS A KID,
LIFE WAS ALL ABOUT
WHAT'S NEXT.
I WAS, LIKE,
"SEVENTH GRADE SUCKS.
WAIT TILL I'M IN
EIGHTH GRADE,"
AND THEN, "FUCK EIGHTH GRADE.
HIGH SCHOOL IS GOING TO ROCK."
LIFE WAS ONE BIG RACE
TO GET TO THE NEXT THING.
[TIRES SQUEALING]
SOMEONE FORGOT TO TELL ME
THAT THE FINISH LINE WAS 18.
THERE ARE PEOPLE
WHO ARE ALWAYS ON TIME.
GEORGE,
YOU'RE GOING TO MISS THE BUS.
I HATE THOSE PEOPLE.
I WAS NOT ON TIME...
BOOKS.
EVER, FOR ANYTHING.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT MY DEAL WAS.
I WAS LATE FROM THE START.
[JOY]:  WHERE
THE HELL IS SHE?
[GEORGE]:
LATE BEFORE THE START.
OH, IS THAT YOU,
GEORGIA?
[JOY]:  GET...
OUT...
NOW!
STOP! STOP!
LATE WAS JUST WHO I WAS.
STOP! ASSHOLE.
THE THING ABOUT LATE
IS YOU ALWAYS FEEL, WELL...
RUSHED.
LATE SUCKS.
YEAH, WELL,
YOU RESCHEDULE THAT, DIANE,
BECAUSE I'M MAKING
THIS FLIGHT, ALL RIGHT?
NO, I DON'T WANT
TO GO TOMORROW.
I WANT TO GO TODAY,
AND WHEN I GET TO ARUBA,
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M GOING TO DO?
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING.
OKAY?
BUT I WANT E-MAIL IN MY HUT...
AND A FAX.
NO. NO, NO, NO.
YOU TELL THEM
TO PUT A FAX IN MY HUT.
OKAY?
CAN YOU MOVE? HUH?
HAS ANYONE SEEN KIFFANY?
WHO ARE
ALL THESE PEOPLE?
WHY ARE THEY
HERE?
AND WHEN WILL THEY
GO AWAY?
THIS IS BULLSHIT.
I'M NOT GOING TO
WAIT AROUND ALL DAY.
I COULD, BUT...
I WON'T.
WHERE ARE YOU
OFF TO?
POST OFFICE.
READ 'EM...
AND REAP.
OH, MY GOD.
I KNOW THIS GUY.
I KNOW MY REAP.
"H. SORIANO."
YOUR DEAR PAL, "H."
HARRY? HENRY?
HANK? HOHO?
HORATIO?
THAT'S ALL I GOT.
HERMAN.SHIT.
HERM WORKS FOR
MERCURY MESSENGERS,
AND HE USED TO,
YOU KNOW, DO A BIT
OF EXTRA COURIER JOBS
ON THE SIDE,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
HE OWES ME 200 BUCKS.
MERCURY MESSENGERS.
THEY HAVE THAT
CUTE COMMERCIAL.
♪ IF YOU GOT A PACKAGE
BUT YOU GOT NO TIME ♪
♪ USE MERCURY
♪ AND YOU'LL BE
♪ JUST FINE
♪ MERCURY
[BOTH]: WHOOSH!
A LITTLE EARLY FOR
THE ANDREWS SISTERS.
HEY, I REAPED ONE OF THEM.
I CAN'T REMEMBER WHICH ONE.
THIS IS ALL THE WAY DOWNTOWN,
AND I WANT A BLUEBERRY MUFFIN.
[RUBE]: I GOT TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING, MASON.
I'M REAL TIRED OF YOU
SHOWING UP BY THE
SKIN OF YOUR TEETH.
I GET THERE, DON'T I?
BARELY.
WHEN I SEE YOU REAPING
LIKE A FUCKING PROFESSIONAL.
WITH A SCYTHE.
A WATCH WOULD BE A START.
[MASON]: ALL RIGHT.
I'LL GET THERE EARLY.
FUCK THE FUCKING
BLUEBERRY MUFFINS.
I'VE BEEN REAPING
EARLIER THESE DAYS.
IT'S A LOT LESS
STRESSFUL.
[DAISY]: I NEVER RUSH.
IF I SEE SOMEONE
RUNNING,
I JUST ASSUME
THEY'RE A LOSER.
UNLESS THEY'RE A RUNNER.
YEAH, EVEN THEN.
ESPECIALLY THEN.
I'M NOT SAYING
GET THERE EARLY.
I'M JUST SAYING DON'T BE LATE.
BLOODY HELL.
[MAN]: MISS! MISS!
CAN WE GET SOME
SERVICE OVER HERE?
I SEE YOU. I'LL BE THERE
IN JUST A MINUTE.
WHAT CAN I GET FOR YOU?
[ALL ORDERING SIMULTANEOUSLY]
LET'S TRY AGAIN.
I'LL COME BACK.
NO! I NEED OATMEAL.
AIRPORT REAP
AT RUSH HOUR.
I'M BONED.
I KNOW WHERE HERM HANGS OUT.
I'LL SHOW RUBE EARLY.
I'LL GET THERE
SO FUCKING EARLY,
I'LL REAP HIM TWICE.
[DAISY]: I CAN'T HANG AROUND
EITHER.
ARE YOU COMING, GEORGIA?
I'M ALREADY
LATE FOR WORK.
20 MINUTES
ISN'T GOING TO KILL ME.
AGAIN.
HOW ABOUT SOME OATMEAL
THIS MORNING?
PLEASE.
WITH RAISINS.
ON THE HOUSE, SWEETIE.
GOOD THINGS COME
TO THOSE WHO WAIT.
WHERE ARE MY KEYS?
REGGIE, HAVE YOU SEEN MY KEYS?
NO.
WHERE ARE
MY F-ING KEYS?
TRY YOUR F-ING PURSE.
REGGIE,
DON'T SAY "F-ING."
WHY ARE YOU
DRESSED LIKE THAT?
I HAVE A MEETING.
DID YOU EAT SOMETHING?
WITH A...
WITH A LAWYER.
PLEASE EAT SOMETHING, HMM?
OATMEAL?
OH, CEREAL. FINE.
WHO'S PICKING YOU UP
THIS MORNING?
MRS. STUART.
DID YOU DO SOMETHING WRONG?
MY DIVORCE LAWYER.
IS DAD GOING TO BE THERE?
YES.
I'M GOING TO TAKE YOU
TO BAND PRACTICE AFTER SCHOOL,
SO DON'T DAWDLE
ON THE WAY HOME.
I DON'T WANT TO
BE IN THE BAND.
REGGIE, PLEASE.
OUR AGREEMENT WAS
ONE SCHOOL ACTIVITY.
THE BAND IS FOR LOSERS.
REGGIE.
MY DAUGHTER IS NOT A LOSER.
I DIDN'T SAY I WAS.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK,
I CAN'T HAVE
THIS CONVERSATION RIGHT NOW.
I'M LATE.
SO GO.
[JOY]: I PAID
FOR DRUM LESSONS
AND A BAND UNIFORM
AND YOU'RE
JOINING THE BAND.[DOOR CLOSING]
I'M NOT JOINING
THE F-ING BAND.
[WHISTLING SOFTLY]
NEXT.
[GEORGE]:  THE NICE THING
ABOUT WORKING AT HAPPY TIME
WAS THAT MY DAY
HAD ITS OWN RHYTHM.
SURE, THINGS GOT BUSY,
BUT THE MORNING WAS MINE.
SHOW UP LATE.
STARE AT SCREEN.
SWIVEL CHAIR.
SIP COFFEE.
REPEAT.
STARE AT SCREEN.
SWIVEL--
I NEED TO GIVE YOU
A WARNING.
WHAT? I WAS ON TIME.
I'M WORKING.
YOU WERE NOT ON TIME.
CHECK IT OUT, MILLIE.
PROBLEM AT 2 O'CLOCK.
THAT'S 10 O'CLOCK.
NO WONDER
YOU'RE ALWAYS LATE.
[GEORGE]: WHO IS IT?
ED BARPHIN,
MANAGEMENT CONSULTANT.
HE'S HERE TO MONITOR
HAPPY TIME'S EFFICIENCY.
I DON'T LIKE
ANYTHING ABOUT HIM.
IOM GOING TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING PERSONAL,
AND IN THE STRICTEST
CONFIDENCE.
[GEORGE]:  PLEASE,
NOT ANYTHING ABOUT HYGIENE.
I HAVE A MOLE.
EW.
IS IT CANCEROUS?
NOT THAT KIND OF MOLE,
YOU SILLY GOOSE.
I KNOW A MUCKETY-MUCK
IN THE HEAD OFFICE.
HE TELLS ME THINGS.
WHAT KIND OF THINGS?
CORPORATE INTRIGUE, MILLIE.
HE KNOWS
WHAT THEIR PLANS ARE FOR ME.
HE DOES?
SHOULD WE GIVE HIM
A CODE NAME?
WHO?MY BIG MOLE.
EW!
SURE.WHAT SHOULD WE CALL HIM?
MOLEY MOLERSTEIN.
MOLEY RINGWALD.
FRED...
TELLS ME I'M IN LINE
FOR A SUBSTANTIAL RAISE
IF THEY SEE I RUN
AN EFFICIENT SHIP.
GREAT.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN TO ME?
WORK FAST TODAY.
CRACK THE WHIP.
I CAN DO THAT.
OH, LOOK AT THIS GUY.
THESE MANAGEMENT
CONSULTANTS,
THEY'RE ALL REAPERS.
WHAT?
THEY HAND OUT PINK SLIPS
LIKE THEY'RE PARTY FAVORS.
CAN I COUNT ON YOU TODAY,
MILLIE?
YOU CAN.
I WILL KICK
SOME RIGHTEOUS ASS
BEFORE THE END OF BUSINESS.
PRAISE THE LORD.
HOW'S EVERYTHING GOING,
MS. HERBIG?
EVERYONE CALLS ME D.H.
IT'S FASTER.
GOING GREAT.
RIGHT, MILLIE?
RIGHT...
D.H.
[DELORES]: MM-HMM.
[GEORGE]:  MORE LIKE B.S.
MORNING, JOY.
SORRY TO KEEP YOU
WAITING.
AS LONG AS THE METER
ISN'T RUNNING.
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
UH, CAN I GET YOU
ANYTHING?
COFFEE? TEA? WATER?
DIVORCE, TO GO.
I KNOW THIS IS HARD.
EXPENSIVE. NOT THAT HARD.
THEN TODAY SHOULD BE PAINLESS.
ALL WE NEED TO DO
IS GO OVER THE FINAL REVISIONS
WITH BOTH PARTIES,
AND THEN YOU SIGN
ON THE DOTTED LINE
AND YOU'RE DONE WITH HIM.
GOOD.GOOD.
HENS PROBABLY
GOING TO BE LATE, YOU KNOW.
HMM.
JUST BECAUSE HE KNOWS
IT DRIVES ME NUTS.
MAY I ASK YOU
SOMETHING PERSONAL?
OFF THE CLOCK.
SURE, KAREN.
WHY ARE YOU STILL
WEARING YOUR RING?
BECAUSE I'M NOT DIVORCED.
YOU PEOPLE HAVE YOUR RITUALS,
AND I HAVE MINE.
HMM.
MIND IF I START THE CLOCK?
START THE CLOCK.
HERM...
WHERE THE FUCK ARE YOU, HERM?
[SCATTERED CHEERS]
'SUP?
WHAT'S UP?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
DO ANY OF YOU CHAPS
KNOW AN H. SORIANO?
HE'S A SKINNY DUDE
WITH A COUPLE OF TATTOOS?
WE'RE ALL SKINNY DUDES
WITH A COUPLE OF TATS.
YES, YOU ARE.
YES.
IS IT POSSIBLE THAT HERM
GOES BY ANOTHER HANDLE?
HANDLE?
WE'RE NOT TRUCKERS, MAN.
LOOK, I NEED TO
FIND HERM, NOW.
I KNOW
HE HANGS OUT HERE.
I OWE HIM MONEY.
I HAVE TO GIVE IT TO HIM NOW.
CHILL, DUDE.
HERM'S ON HIS WAY.
HERM.
HERM! H...
OH, SWEET CHRIST.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
YOU DON'T EVER FORGET.
[MOCKING LAUGHTER]
[MASON]: I'M OKAY.
[BUZZES]
GOOD MORNING.
HOW ARE YOU THIS MORNING?
NO HABLA INGLES.
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN TO HAWAII?
AY, DIOS MIO.
I JUST GOT BACK
FROM A VACATION IN HAWAII.
I'M HERE TO PICK UP MY MAIL.
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT
IT WAS GOING TO BE SUNNY,
BUT IT RAINED.
MY SON TOOK ME
ON A CRUISE.
ALL THE SHRIMP
YOU CAN EAT
AT EVERY MEAL,
EVEN BREAKFAST.
ARE YOU MEXICAN?
ACTUALLY, I'M FROM NEW YORK.
I'VE NEVER BEEN TO NEW YORK.
I DON'T THINK
I'D LIKE IT, THOUGH,
ALL THOSE
TALL BUILDINGS
AND EVERYONE RUNNING AROUND.
ALTHOUGH I WOULD LIKE
TO MEET MATT LAUER.
YOU LOOK A LITTLE LIKE HIM,
ONLY OLDER AND ANGRIER.
HAVE YOU EVER
BEEN TO HAWAII?
[LIGHT JAZZ PLAYING]
SWEETHEART.
GOD LOVE YOU FOR COMING.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
A FABULOUS TIME.
I'M SURE I WILL, SHERRI.
LET'S GET YOU A NAME TAG.
I FEEL LIKE A CHRISTIAN
IN THE COLISEUM.
WHAT EXACTLY IS GOING ON HERE?
PRETTY AND FUNNY.
THE WHOLE PACKAGE.
YOU'RE GOING TO
KILL IN THERE.
TELL ME YOUR NAME, DOLL.
UM, DAISY. DAISY ADAIR.
OH. FIRST NAMES ONLY.
DISCOURAGES THE
STALKER ELEMENT.
DAISY.
RIGHT. HERE WE GO.
BREAK SOME HEARTS.
I'M RETURNING LYDIA'S CALL.
IT'S MILLIE FROM HAPPY TIME.
HI, LYDIA.
YOU'VE TEMPED FOR THEM BEFORE.
THERE'S A DRESS CODE,
AND YOUR SKIRT NEEDS
TO ACTUALLY COVER YOUR ASS.
I DON'T CARE
WHERE YOUR TATTOO IS.
YOU CANNOT SHOW CRACK
AT THE OFFICE.
I HAVE TO CALL YOU BACK.
MAY I HELP YOU WITH SOMETHING,
MR. BARPHIN?
WAS THAT CALL
OF A BUSINESS NATURE?
THE WAY D.H.
RUNS THINGS AROUND HERE,
THERE ISN'T ANY ANOTHER KIND.
MAY I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
THAT IS A QUESTION.
WOULD YOU LIKE
TO ASK ME ANOTHER ONE?
DO YOU ROUTINELY
USE OFF-COLOR LANGUAGE
AS PART
OF YOUR BUSINESS LEXICON?
SOMETIMES OFF-COLOR LANGUAGE
IS THE MOST EFFICIENT WAY
TO CONVEY AN IDEA.
AS IN,
"GET THE FUCK AWAY
FROM MY CUBICLE."
I HAVE AN OBSERVATION.
L.T.H.I.
LOVE TO HEAR IT.
WHEN YOU MAKE A CALL,
YOU DO NOT NEED TO SAY,
"RETURNING SO-AND-SO'S CALL."
YOU CAN JUST SAY, "RETURNING."
SAVES TIME.
I WANTED TO ASK,
"SAVES TIME FOR WHAT?"
BUT I JUST SAID...
THANK YOU.WELCOME.
SAVE YOUR FUCKING BREATH,
YOU WORM.
WELCOME TO "MAKE YOUR MOVE."
EACH DATE IS TWO MINUTES.
NO TALK ABOUT WORK,
AND FIRST NAMES ONLY.
[BELL RINGS]OKAY. MAKE YOUR MOVE!
YOW.
DAISY.
HELLO, DAISY.
PRETTIEST FLOWER
IN THE GARDEN.
SO, DAISY,
WE'VE ONLY GOT TWO MINUTES.
ANYTHING
YOU WANT TO ASK "THE KID?"
[DAISY]: YES, UM...
WHAT'S, UH...
WHAT'S YOUR LAST NAME?
BABE, LAST NAMES
SPELL COMMITMENT.
I'M ALL ABOUT THE HERE,
THE NOW,
THE YOU AND ME
ATTACKING SOME BEDSPRINGS.
[SQUEAKS]
LAST NAME.[GRUNTS]
MANDELL.
THIS IS FUN.
SWEETIE,
NO PHYSICAL THREATS
TO THE GENTLEMEN.
I NEED THE REPEAT CUSTOMERS.
I'M NEW.
OKAY.
OKAY, OKAY.
WALK ME THROUGH
MY SPA TREATMENTS.
[REVS ENGINE]
YEAH.
UH-UH.
NO, NOT THE MUD WRAP.
I WANT THE HOT ROCKS.
NO NEED TO TRAVEL 4,000 MILES
TO HAVE SOMEBODY
SHOVE MUD UP MY ASS.
COME ON!
[HONKS]
COME--
MOVE IT!
[BICYCLE BELL RINGS]
[STRAINING]
[WOMAN ON P.A.]:
PASSENGERS ARRIVING
ON FLIGHT 127 FROM HONG KONG
MAY PICK UP THEIR BAGGAGE
FROM CAROUSEL NUMBER ONE.
MRS. WILLIAMS, YOUR CHILDREN
HAVE BEEN FOUND...
EXCUSE ME. HELLO.
CAN I GET
EVERYBODY'S ATTENTION?
EXCUSE ME, MA'AM.
CAN I GET EVERYBODY'S
ATTENTION?
MY NAME IS WILLIAM GARRATT,
AND IT IS MY PLEASURE TO
ADDRESS THE BAGGAGE SITUATION
ON FLIGHT 127 FROM HONG KONG.
[FRENCH ACCENT]
IF I DO NOT GET MY TRUNK,
I AM FUCKED.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
FUCKED.
YES, MA'AM, I DO,
BUT I ALSO UNDERSTAND
THAT ANGER AND FOUL LANGUAGE
IS NOT GOING TO MAKE
THIS PROCESS GO ANY FASTER,
AND WHEN YOU
GET YOUR TRUNK
AND YOU'RE ON YOUR WAY
IN A FEW MINUTES,
YOU MIGHT BE WONDERING
WHY YOU MADE SUCH A FUSS.
I HAVE BEEN WAITING HERE
ONE HOUR!
MA'AM,
CAN YOU STEP BACK
AND CALM DOWN?
BECAUSE I'M GETTING READY
TO DO MY THING.
ONE...
TWO...
THREE.
[CAROUSEL BEEPS]
EARPIECE TO THE
BAGGAGE HANDLERS
ON THE TARMAC?
SO YOU DIDN'T BUY
MY ZEN-LIKE CALM, HUH?
I BOUGHT YOUR ZEN-LIKE CALM.
I JUST DIDN'T BUY
THE MAGIC TRICK.
LISTEN,
I DON'T MEAN TO ALARM YOU,
BUT I NEED TO SEE YOUR
PASSENGER MANIFEST, PLEASE.
SWEETHEART,
ONLY A GUN TO MY HEAD
WOULD ALARM ME,
AND NOT EVEN THEN.
EXCUSE ME.
I NEED THE
FOLLOWING PASSENGERS
TO IDENTIFY
THEMSELVES, PLEASE.
PASSENGER JONES.
[JONES]: HERE
PASSENGER THIBODEAUX.
THANK YOU FOR
YOUR COOPERATION,
AND HAVE A NICE DAY,
AND THANK YOU, SIR.
THANK YOU.
EXCUSE ME.
MAY I SEE YOUR PASSPORT,
PLEASE?
IT'S JUST
A ROUTINE CHECK.
BECAUSE THIS IS WHAT I NEED.
MORE STUPID AMERICANS
TO KEEP ME FROM
WHERE I'M GOING.
EVERYONE'S DOING WHAT THEY CAN
TO GET YOU
WHERE YOU'RE GOING, MISS.
YOU JUST NEED TO STAY CALM.
CALM IS FOR LOSERS.
I HAVE PLACES TO GO.
THEN YOU GO, BABY.
ALLEZ, ALLEZ.
TU ES VRAIMENT UNE VACHE,HUH?
[BELL RINGS]
JEFF...
ALLEN?
NO.
WE SHOULDN'T WASTE TIME, JEFF.
YOU AND I? NO CONNECTION.
WHAT?
I DON'T LIKE MOUSTACHES.
OH. NO.
I DON'T EVEN REALLY LIKE IT.
I WAS PLANNING ON SHAVING IT.
SERIOUSLY.
I ALMOST SHAVED IT OFF
RIGHT BEFORE I CAME.
EVEN IF YOU SHAVED IT,
I'D ALWAYS SEE IT.
REALLY?YEAH.
DATING, IT'S ALL
ABOUT FIRST IMPRESSIONS,
SNAP JUDGMENTS,
AND THIS, JEFF,
THIS THING BETWEEN YOU AND I,
IT'S NOT POWERFUL.
THIS IS NOT MEANT TO BE.
[BELL RINGS]
NICE MEETING YOU.
[DOOR OPENS]
HI.
UM, THIS IS IT.
REGGIE'S BAND UNIFORM.
YOU TOLD ME
TO PICK IT UP.
HOW DOES IT LOOK?
IT'S PRETTY ADORABLE.
DOES IT HAVE ONE OF THE HATS?
OH. YEAH.
CHIN STRAP AND EVERYTHING.
OH, MY GOD.
EPAULETS. EPAULETS.
COULDN'T YOU JUST DIE?
OKAY, WE'RE ALL HERE.
LET'S GET GOING.
I HAVE COPIES
FOR EVERYONE.
IF YOU'LL JUST
TAKE A MINUTE,
YOU'LL NOTICE
THE REVISIONS
ARE IN BOLD,
AND IF THERE ARE
ANY QUESTIONS--
YOU'RE TAKING REGGIE
FOR CHRISTMAS?
WELL, WE'RE GOING TO MEXICO
FOR THANKSGIVING.
TERRIFIC.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
GOING TO CANCUN?
DOES IT REALLY MATTER
WHERE I'M GOING?
I'M GOING.
SO I GET REGGIE
FOR THANKSGIVING,
WHEN SHE HATES THE FOOD?
THAT'S JUST THE WAY
IT WORKED OUT.
SO YOU GET TO
HAVE OUR DAUGHTER
ON THE HOLIDAY WHEN
SHE OPENS PRESENTS,
AND I GET HER FOR THE ONE
WHERE SHE THROWS UP?
WHAT DO YOU WANT, JOY?
CAN I BORROW YOUR PEN?
THE FANCY ONE IN YOUR POCKET.
DO YOU MIND?
BE MY GUEST.
YOU CAN USE MINE IF YOU LIKE.
THANK YOU.
[BELL RINGS]
HELLO THERE, JACK.RIGHT.
SO, ARE YOU HAVING
SOME NICE DATES?
ARE YOU TRYING
TO DUMP ME ALREADY?
NO, JUST MAKING CHIT-CHAT.
I BET YOU'RE DYING TO DATE
THAT HUMP OVER THERE.
WELL, HE IS HANDSOME,
BUT I LOOK FOR MANY
OTHER QUALITIES IN A MAN.
IS YOUR LAST NAME ALLEN?
I KNOW FOR A FACT
THAT THAT GUY HAS HERPES.
FACT.EASY THERE, TIGER.
YOU DESPISE MEN, DON'T YOU?
WHAT?
YOU COME HERE
BECAUSE YOU HATE MEN.
YOU'RE A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN
WHO HATES MEN.
GOD,
I HOPE YOUR LAST NAME'S ALLEN.
IT'S NOT.
ALL THE WOMEN I KNOW HATE MEN.
NO, THEY JUST HATE YOU.
[BELL RINGS]
MARTY,
CALL THE MESSENGER SERVICE,
FIND OUT WHAT'S
KEEPING THEM.
STEPHANIE, THE COPIER
NEEDS TONER,
AND...
YOU.
I DON'T KNOW YOUR NAME.
I'M THE SANDWICH BOY.
WELL, SANDWICH BOY,
WHERE ARE THE SANDWICHES?
IN RECEPTION.
ARE THERE HUNGRY PEOPLE
IN RECEPTION?
NO, THEY'RE IN HERE, STARVING.
THE TED
HAS NOT BEEN
GIVEN AN TASK.
THE TED IS TASKLESS.
THE TED
IS TO REMAIN WITH MILLIE.
THE TED MUST MAKE
MILLIE LAUGH.
KEEP YOUR STATION TUNED
TO CHANNEL TED.
IT'S ALL TED, ALL THE TIME.
T-N-T.
TED 'N' TED--
TED ON MUTE.
I FELT A LITTLE LIKE RUBE
HANDING OUT POST-ITS.
LIKE DEATH,
WE WERE
ON A PRETTY TIGHT SCHEDULE.
LET
DON'T DILLY-DALLY.
TIME IS MONEY, PEOPLE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I JUST SAID, "DILLY-DALLY."
I FEEL DIRTY.
I DON'T LIKE
THESE STAMPS.
DO YOU HAVE SOMETHING ELSE?
I REMEMBER SOMETHING
WITH AMELIA EARHART.
I LOVED HER.
I REAPED HER.
[TRICKLING]
[MOANS]
WHILE EVERYONE MAY AGREE
THAT TIME FLIES
WHEN YOU'RE HAVING FUN,
IT IS A LITTLE-KNOWN FACT
THAT EVEN WHEN
YOU'RE NOT HAVING FUN,
TIME STILL CAN FLY...
AND IT FLIES COACH.
[TICKING]
THIS IS A JOKE, RIGHT?
SO, WHAT WAS MY TIME?
NICE.
AND EVEN THOUGH
TIMES KNOWS HOW TO FLY,
IT REMEMBERS HOW TO CRAWL.
HI. CAN I CUT IN?
EXCUSE ME.
YOU LOOK GREAT.THANK YOU.
WHAT A DAY I'VE HAD.
WOULD YOU
HOLD MY SPOT, PLEASE?
AFTERNOON, LADIES.
ARE YOU TWO OLD FRIENDS?
UH, HER DAUGHTER'S
IN MY SON'S CLASS.
I HAVE A QUESTION FOR YOU.
IS EVERYONE IN THIS LINE
AN ASSHOLE?
EXCUSE ME?
IS EVERYONE YOU JUST
CUT IN FRONT OF
AN ASSHOLE?
NO.
SO IT'S JUST YOU, THEN?
I HAVE CHILDREN IN THE CAR.
I GOT A CAKE IN THE OVEN.
HE'S GOT THREE MINUTES LEFT
ON THE METER.
SHE'S GOT A LUNCH MEETING.
WE ALL HAVE A FINITE
AMOUNT OF TIME.
NOW, GET IN THE BACK
OF THE LINE,
AND DON'T USE YOUR CHILDREN
LIKE THAT. IT'S SHAMEFUL.
[BELL RINGS]
[GEORGE]:  IT'S BEEN SAID
THAT TIME AND TIDE
WAIT FOR NO MAN.
NEITHER DOES DAISY.
A WORD ABOUT THE ASCOT.
YOU NEED TO BE REALLY STYLISH
OR REALLY RICH
TO PULL THAT OFF,
OR ARE YOU GAY?
[BELL RINGS]
NO.[BELL RINGS]
I SMELL AN OBSESSION
WITH UFOs.
I'M NOT OBSESSED WITH UFOs.
OKAY.
BUT I DID COME HERE IN ONE.
BIG ONE.
WOW.
YO, CUP O' NOODLES.
LET'S MOVE IT ALONG
HERE.
THE TED HAS
LOW BLOOD SUGAR.
SHUT UP, TED.
THE TED WILL IGNORE
WHAT HE WOULD
NORMALLY TAKE
TO BE FIGHTING WORDS.
THE TED NEEDS
TO CHILL.
[MOANS]
I'M OKAY.
JE N'AI PAS ENCORE
MA VALISE.
OUI. CA FAIT UNE HEURE
QUE JE SUIS ICI.
JUST HAND YOUR TICKET
TO THAT GENTLEMAN OVER THERE,
AND YOU CAN BE ON YOUR WAY.
MAN, YOU GOT
THE PATIENCE OF JOB.
THE AIRPORT'S NOT
A HAPPY PLACE FOR
A LOT OF PEOPLE,
BUT I'M HAPPY.
I BELIEVE THAT TENDS
TO RUB OFF ON PEOPLE.
I WOULDN'T KNOW.
I DON'T WORK THAT WAY.
YOU ARE A SHOOT FIRST
AND ASK QUESTIONS LATER,
AREN'T YOU?
I REALLY AM.
WELL, I BELIEVE THAT
IT'S HARDER TO BE HAPPY
WHEN YOU HAVE A GUN
ON YOUR BELT.
MAKES ANGER
A MUCH EASIER CHOICE.
YOU USED TO BE ON THE JOB?
NO.
NOT YOUR JOB.
I WASN'T ALWAYS A...
CALM MAN.
PEOPLE SUFFERED.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
I THINK I DO.
[SNARLING]
IT WAS REALLY GOOD
MEETING YOU, WILLIAM.
NICE TO MEET YOU, OFFICER.
NEXT.
AFTERNOON.
I'M HERE TO PICK UP
A PACKAGE.
I'LL JUST TAKE A MINUTE.TAKE TWO.
WELL, THIS IS INTERESTING.
WHAT'S THAT?
THIS HAS BEEN IN
THE DEAD LETTER OFFICE
FOR A WHILE.
WHY DIDN'T THIS
GET TO WHERE IT WAS GOING?
I WOULDN'T
KNOW THAT, SIR.
WELL, THIS WAS SENT
A LONG TIME AGO.
PERHAPS THE PEOPLE MOVED.
NO, THEY DIDN'T MOVE.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED, SIR.
I WASN'T THERE.
THIS IS ALMOST 80 YEARS...
80 YEARS OLD.
THIS IS UNACCEPTABLE.
SIR, IT MIGHT BE UNACCEPTABLE,
BUT IT IS THE WAY IT IS.
IT WAS IN
THE DEAD LETTER OFFICE.
IT TOOK A LONG WHILE
TO MAKE ITS WAY BACK,
BUT NOW YOU HAVE IT.
WELL, THIS IS A MISTAKE.
IT CAME BACK.
THIS IS A TERRIBLE MISTAKE.
ON BEHALF OF THE
U.S. POSTAL SYSTEM,
I APOLOGIZE
FOR ANY INCONVENIENCE
THIS MIGHT HAVE CAUSED YOU
OR YOUR FAMILY.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
HI, JAMES.
HI, DAISY.
WHAT'S YOUR LAST NAME, JAMES?
BOND. JAMES BOND.
I THOUGHT THAT MIGHT BE FUNNY.
NO, IT'S FUNNY.
IT'S FUNNY.
I JUST, UM...
I'VE BEEN HERE A WHILE.
YEAH, ME TOO.
17 TIMES, ACTUALLY.
WOW.
YOU MUST BE GETTING
VERY GOOD AT IT.
I'M TERRIBLE.
NO ONE EVER WRITES ME DOWN.
WELL, MAYBE YOU JUST
HAVEN'T MET THE RIGHT GIRL.
ARE YOU THE RIGHT GIRL, DAISY?
I KNOW, TWO MINUTES IS TOUGH.
EVERYONE LIKES TO TALK,
AND I LIKE TO LISTEN.
I GUESS IT'S HARD
TO REMEMBER SOMEONE
WHO JUST LISTENS.
WELL, I'LL REMEMBER YOU.
I HOPE SO, DAISY.
I'VE REALLY ENJOYED SPENDING--[BELL RINGS]
[SHERRI]: MAKE YOUR MOVES,
SPEED DATERS! HURRY UP.
SEE YOU, JAMES BOND.
MY NAME'S NOT REALLY BOND.
I KNOW.
IT'S ALLEN.
DAISY,
YOU HAVE A REALLY NICE SMILE.
GOODBYE.BYE.
[GEORGE]:
EVERYONE SAYS LIVE IN THE NOW,
BUT THAT'S BULLSHIT.
I MEAN,
WHO LIVES IN THE MOMENT?
WE'RE TOO BUSY THINKING
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENS NEXT...
OR WHAT DIDN'T HAPPEN AT ALL.
HAVE I EVER SAT
IN AN AISLE SEAT, DIANE? HUH?
BUSINESS CLASS,
RIGHT SIDE WINDOW, BULKHEAD.
WHAT ARE YOU, NEW? HUH?
LET'S GO.
LET'S MAKE THINGS
HAPPEN HERE, DIANE.
COME ON.
I KNOW IT DOESN'T
SEEM LIKE IT,
BUT YOU ARE
IN GOOD HANDS.
[CAROUSEL BEEPING]
[CAROUSEL CLANGS OFF]
OH, COME ON, NOW, LADY.
YOU CAN'T DO THAT,
MA'AM.
[LOUD THUMP]
[ONLOOKERS GASP]
ZUT ALORS.
THIS IS VERY
INCONVENIENT.
LADY, YOU'RE DEAD.
YES, AND I AM SURE
THERE ARE MANY OTHER
DEAD PEOPLE UP THERE
TRYING TO TAKE MY PLACE.
LET'S GO.
C'EST LA VIE.
[CAROUSEL BEEPING]
[GEORGE]:  WATCHING
A REALLY EFFICIENT SYSTEM
IN ACTION
SOMETIMES JUST KNOCKS YOU OUT,
AND SOMETIMES
IT JUST MAKES YOU SICK.
THE TIME CARD.
MAKES IT A SNAP TO MONITOR
EVERYONE'S COMINGS AND GOINGS.
PEOPLE ARE WORKING,
AND WHEN THEY'RE NOT,
YOU KNOW ABOUT IT.
I LOVE IT.
IT'S NOT VERY...
PERSONAL.
EXACTLY.
IT REDUCES THE AMOUNT
OF TIME YOU NEED
TO TALK
TO YOUR EMPLOYEES.
WELL, THAT'S JUST...
FANTASTIC.
[GEORGE]:  ON THE CLOCK.
ALWAYS ON THE CLOCK.
NO MATTER HOW QUICKLY
EVERYONE DID THEIR JOB TODAY,
SOMEONE SOMEWHERE
WOULD BE PUNCHING OUT
BEFORE 5:00.
COME ON, REGGIE.
LET'S SEE.
[REGGIE]: I'M NOT GOING.
LET ME JUST SEE
WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
I LOOK LIKE A GEEK.
ALL RIGHT.
I KNOW THAT IS NOT TRUE.
LOOK,
I PAID GOOD MONEY FOR THIS.
YOU HAVE TO AT LEAST SHOW ME.
NOW.
PLEASE?
OH.
YOU ARE SO CUTE.
BLAH.
I'M TAKING A PICTURE.
NO WAY.OH, YEAH.
NO, TOO LATE.
I HAVE TO GET A CAMERA.
JUST STAY RIGHT THERE.
I HATE THIS.
STAY RIGHT THERE
BEFORE IT GETS ALL CRUMPLED UP
IN THE CAR.
SHUT UP.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, I WANT ONE
WITH THE HAT ON...
REGGIE?
AW...
[PANTING AND MOANING]
UH...
WELL, SOMEONE'S POPULAR.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE
A VERY BUSY GIRL.
BUSY, BUSY, BUSY.
JAMES.
NOBODY
WROTE MY NAME DOWN.
I DID.
YOU WERE JUST TRYING
TO BE NICE.
NO, I REALLY LIKED YOU.
I LIKED YOU TOO.
YOU'D REALLY
GO OUT WITH ME?
SURE.
IN A NEW YORK MINUTE.
WHO EVER THOUGHT
OF THE CONCEPT
OF KNOWING SOMEONE
IN TWO MINUTES?
YEAH.
IT TAKES EVEN LESS TIME
THAN THAT.
WHY DON'T YOU
COME WITH ME, JAMES?
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
I DIDN'T JUMP.
I SLIPPED.
I'M WAITING FOR OUR DATE, SIR.
YOU WERE THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL WOMAN THERE.
I KNOW.
SEE, WE'RE NOT TOO LATE.
EVERYONE'S
STILL GETTING THERE.
I DON'T WANT TO DO IT.
I WANT TO GO HOME.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE FUN.
YOU DON'T KNOW THAT.
SEE, IF YOU KEEP WAITING
ON THE SIDELINES...
THIS IS A REALLY...
PRECIOUS TIME.
I DON'T... I DON'T WANT YOU
TO BE LEFT OUT.
I WANT TO JUST...
HELP YOU RUN IN THERE.
YOU KNOW?
GEORGE WOULDN'T HAVE
PUT THIS CRAPPY UNIFORM ON.
I...I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T WANT TO WEAR GLASSES
ANYMORE.
WHAT?EVERYONE CALLS ME
HARRIET POTTER.
I DON'T LIKE IT.
OKAY.
IS THERE ANY...
ANYTHING ELSE YOU WANT TO...
YOU WANT TO TELL ME?
ANYTHING?
WE COULD JUST
TAKE LITTLE MINUTE.
FORGET IT. I'M LATE.
[CAR APPROACHING]
REGGIE!
WHAT?
DON'T JUST RUN
ACROSS THE STREET
WITHOUT LOOKING.
JESUS FUCKING CHRIST!
WHAT THE HELL WERE YOU
THINKING ABOUT?
I'M SORRY.
REGGIE, I'M SORRY.
JUST...JUST...
JUST PLEASE BE CAREFUL.
OKAY.HEY.
CAN I JUST TAKE ONE PICTURE?
YOU LOOK SO BEAUTIFUL.
I'M LATE.
OH, MY GOD. WHAT HAVE I DONE?
I'M A STUPID MAN.
[MAN]: WHAT'S UP, DUDE?
HERM.
MASON, MASON.
MASON, YOU DON'T
LOOK SO GOOD, MAN.
I'M OKAY.
I OWE YOU SOME MONEY, DON'T I?
HERM, HERM, HERM, HERM.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT?
THAT DOESN'T SOUND
LIKE THE MASON I KNOW.
YOU SURE YOU'RE
ALL RIGHT, MAN?
I'M ALL RIGHT.
I'M JUST TAKING A BREATHER.
YEAH?
A BREATHER FROM WHAT?
FROM BEING ME.
COME ON, MAN.
GET UP OUT OF THAT GUTTER.
THANKS, MATE.
YOU SURE
YOU DON'T WANT THIS MONEY?
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
I GOT SOME SPEED.
I'LL GIVE YOU THE MONEY.
YOU BUY THE SPEED.
I DON'T WANT IT.
HONESTLY.
ALL RIGHT.
LOOK, I GOT TO GO, MAN.
I GOT TO GET TO THE NEXT DROP.
DUDE FORGOT
HIS STICKS, MAN.
TAKE CARE.I WILL.
HEY, MASON.
WHAT DO YOU CALL A GUY
WHO HANGS OUT
WITH THREE MUSICIANS?
I GIVE UP.
THE DRUMMER.
LATER, MAN.
I GOT TO SCRAMBLE.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
DUDE.DUDE.
OH, MAN!
HEY, THAT'S BRUTAL.
PSST. PSST. HEY, HEY, HEY.
I THINK IT'S GOING
REALLY WELL, DON'T YOU?
I GUESS.
UM, I HAVE
A DOCTOR APPOINTMENT.
OH, FINE.
I CAN JUST SMELL THAT RAISE.
YOU'VE REALLY HUSTLED TODAY,
MILLIE,
AND I APPRECIATE IT.
DON'T YOU THINK
THINGS WERE
A LITTLE STRANGE TODAY?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
NEVER MIND.
I MEAN, I KNOW WE'VE
PICKED UP THE PACE,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY.
"IF YOU'RE SKATING
OVER THIN ICE,
YOU'D BETTER GO FAST."
WHAT IF WE JUST
AVOIDED THE ICE ALTOGETHER?
YO, MILLIE.
WHAT UP, DAWG?
YO, TED.
[TED]: SO, DELORES,
WHEN DO I GET
MY LAST CHECK?
IN ABOUT A WEEK.
WHAT?
I FIRED TED.
I'M TOAST.
BURNT TOAST.
HASTA LUEGO,TED.
TEDMEISTER,
OVER AND OUT.
CHECK, PLEASE,
FOR THE TEDSTER.
WHY DID YOU FIRE TED?
STAY OUT OF IT, MILLIE.
FINE, HE'S
A LITTLE DIFFERENT,
BUT IS THAT ANY REASON
TO FIRE HIM?
TED'S FUNNY.
MAYBE HE DOESN'T
GET AS MUCH WORK DONE
AROUND HERE
AS EVERYONE ELSE,
BUT AT LEAST
HE MAKES LIFE
A LITTLE MORE FUN
AROUND HERE.
THAT HAS TO STAND
FOR SOMETHING.
THE TED IS DEAD.
OH...
IS THE TED DRUNK?
[VOMITING]
TED...
[BELCHES]
GOODBYE, TED.
MILLIE WILL MISS YOU.
WHEN I WAS ALIVE,
I DIDN'T CARE ABOUT TIME.
I DIDN'T THINK ABOUT IT,
AND I GUESS THAT'S WHY
I WAS ALWAYS LATE...
BUT SINCE I DIED, IT'S WEIRD.
I GUESS I WANT TO BE MORE...
ON TIME.
WHOO.
WHAT DID YOU DO?
KNOCK OVER A BANK?
NO.
IS THIS REAL MONEY?
IT WAS,
MANY YEARS AGO.
ARE YOU OKAY?
JUST A LONG DAY.
HAVE YOU HANDLED
YOUR POST-IT YET?
I'M ON MY WAY.
DON'T BE LATE.
I WON'T BE.
DO YOU WANT A RIDE HOME?
I'LL WALK.
[GEORGE]: RUBE.
THANKS.
[GEORGE]:  I HEARD IT
A MILLION TIMES
WHEN I WAS GROWING UP.
"HURRY UP, GEORGIA."
"SEIZE THE DAY, GEORGIA."
AND NO MATTER HOW FAST I WENT,
I JUST KEPT FALLING BEHIND.
I JUST KEPT GETTING
LATER AND LATER,
AND THE WHOLE TIME,
I WAS THINKING, "WHAT'S NEXT?"
I COULDN'T WAIT
FOR WHAT'S NEXT.
MAYBE PEOPLE SHOULD
JUST FIND ONE PRETTY SPOT
AND STAY THERE.
THE FUNNY THING IS
WHEN YOU DIE,
EVERYONE REFERS TO YOU
AS "LATE,"
BUT NOW I KNOW
THAT'S THE ONE EVENT
THAT ALWAYS HAPPENS
RIGHT ON TIME.
[MERCEDES GUY]: WHAT THE FUCK?
ANOTHER RED LIGHT?
DIANE. DIANE.
OVERNIGHT THE BAG, ALL RIGHT?
I DON'T GIVE A SHIT.
LOOK, JUST SOLVE
THE PROBLEM.
I'M 10 FEET
FROM THE AIRPORT.
THIS IS FUCKING RIDICULOUS.
HEY. HELLO.
COULD YOU PUSH
THE LITTLE BUTTON RIGHT THERE?
WHAT?
PUSH THE BUTTON RIGHT--
THE WALK...
CALL ME BACK.
FUCK.
ONCE IS ENOUGH.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR THIS SHIT, ALL RIGHT?
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[PEOPLE SHOUTING]
YOU CAN COME THIS WAY.
I'LL SHOW YOU.
I'M GOING TO NEED
A MINUTE.
[GEORGE]: LET ME KNOW
WHEN YOU'RE READY.
[MERCEDES GUY]:
I GUESS THERE'S NO HURRY.
[MEOWS][MAN]: MURRAY.
[PURR, MEOW]