Now the story of a wealthy
family who lost everything
and the one son who had no
choice but to
keep them all together.
It's Arrested Development.
Michael Bluth
and his family were
meeting with
their new attorney.
Look, this is not
the first time I've
been brought in to
replace Barry Zuckerkorn.
I think I can do for
you everything he did.
Plus, skew younger.
With juries and so forth.
Any other questions?
Yes. How can
you be even cuter in
person than you
are in your ads?
Are you a CEO, CFO or other
executive facing
these or similar charges?
Why should you go to jail for
a crime someone else noticed?
You don't need double-talk.
You need Bob Loblaw.
Bob Loblaw,  no habla Espanol.
Well, we're not here to talk
nonsense to Bob Loblaw.
We need to find out if the
government has a
good case against us.
There was a lot
of proof that my
father was
building houses in Iraq.
Well, your
father claims he was
put up to it by a
British syndicate.
And you've been threatened,
isn't that correct?
It was.
How would you
like someone going
after some stupid
person in your family?
Now back off,
you ( bleep ) ponce!
It's been a week.
Nothing's happened.
Yeah, but you're
not the one stuck
under house arrest
like a sitting duck.
Yeah, that's my father.
That's why we had the meeting
here-- so that he
couldn't interfere.
Interfere? I
ought to pull down
your pants and
spank your ass raw.
I'm sorry. Have we met?
Oh, yes, this
is Larry Mittleman.
He's your father's surrogate.
Surrogate?
That's right,
you dumb ( bleep ).
I hired this guy to wear  a
camera in his hat so he
could be my eyes and ears
while I'm stuck
in this penthouse.
This camera helps me
keep tabs on you idiots,
while this thing
rubs my ankle raw.
I mean, look at this thing.
I can't even go
in the hallway...
- ...without hearing..
...that beep, beep, beep.
That's one of my
partners. Excuse me.
I would like to be
one of your partners.
Do you think he got
that-- the two meanings?
He's running pretty
fast. I think he did.
Well, he was flirting
earlier, I'll tell you that.
Just so you know... I'm
looking to get divorced.
- Are you interested?
- Yes.
Let's call that a half hour.
So you're not the only  one
who's got a date later.
You've got a date?
Her name's Rita. She
teaches children at a
private school and
we're just having lunch.
Oh, lunch? Well,
better bring some dog food.
'Cause all the girls
you date are dogs, and...
Dogs love dog
food, right, Pop?
Shut up, you idiot. I'm
trying to watch the game.
I was trying to
make you laugh, Dad.
That's all I ever wanted.
You know, Gob,
she's not a dog.
It's the just
opposite, actually.
She's exquisitely
beautiful. She's fun,
carefree, smart,
full of surprises.
Including the fact that she
was working with this man--
who was currently
dropping her off for her date.
All this fun
and carefree act is
only going to
fool him for so long.
I'm a big girl.
Yeah. Well, if he
finds out what you really are
he might not make
things so simple for you.
Rita, don't forget your hat.
I know, that might make you
feel she's too good for me.
How do you think I feel?
Bob Loblaw's a handsome,
professional man
and I'm only just a...
well, none of those things.
Okay, Lindsay,
are you forgetting
that I was a
professional twice over--
an analyst and a therapist.
The world's first analrapist.
Yes, and you were almost
arrested for
those business cards.
Yes. No, it did not
look good on paper but I
didn't stop because
of the police inquiries,
I stopped to raise
our little daughter.
But since we have both started
to grow hair in
unexpected places,
I supposed I shall soon be
working as a leading man.
And she may soon start dating.
Maeby had
already started dating.
- All right, see
you tomorrow night
Another date with Steve Holt?
Yeah. We're
getting pretty serious.
They weren't.
She was just avoiding her
real crush on George Michael.
That Steve sure
knows how to please a lady.
Good.
I was helping he
would be gifted sexually.
I guess it
makes sense, you know,
older guys
expect certain things.
They do?
What a fun, sexy time for you.
I'd be very careful
of these British people.
They're going to try
to get their hands on
any evidence they
can to hurt the family.
So you're saying
shred the evidence?
No, that's illegal.
The prosecution is
entitled to that evidence.
Without it, they
don't have a case.
So you're saying
shred the evidence?
That's a felony.
And I certainly couldn't
endorse anything like that.
Got ya.
Wink.
Did you say
"wink" or did you wink?
He said that, too, Dad.
We'll talk soon,
folks. Thank you.
Where you going? Where
is the surrogate going?
Stay there.
I want to see what he's
going to say. Don't leave.
See you, pop.
Gob, instead of trying to
impress your fake father,
maybe you should spend some
time with your real son.
Steve Holt's not my son.
Steve Holt?
With the moron jock?
That's my son, you pothead.
Hey, hey, hey, that's my son.
Wait, so that means   that
Steve Holt is my cousin?
And Maeby's cousin, too.
I guess.
Shoot, I'm late for my date.
At the kennel.
Right.
Sorry. You lobbed that one
right over the plate, Michael.
Home run.
And Michael
hurried to the British
section Orange
County for his date.
...American!
Get out of the road.
Only to find that
Rita had chosen Wee
Britain's one
American-themed restaurant.
Oh, hello. I'm sorry I'm late.
Oh, no bother.
I've been having such
fun on this space shuttle.
Strike one, huh?
Shall we go
ahead and sit down?
Hey, dudes, I'll get you a
couple of 64-ounce colas
to wash down this basket of
doughnut and get
your nachos started.
I guess this is what the
British think of Americans.
- They like our food.
- Whatever do you mean?
Yeah. Uh...
You know, Rita, you're going
to figure this out eventually,
but I have not been on a date
in a long, long time.
- Neither have I.
- I wonder why?
No, I bet men ask
you out constantly.
Not men like you.
I seem to only
meet little boys.
Part of that might be that you
spend your day at a preschool.
And they think the
stupidest things are funny.
Yeah, that's a cultural
problem, is what it is.
You know, your
average American male
is in perpetual
state of adolescence,
you know.
arrested development.
Hey, that's the
name of the show.
No attention span. You know,
can't even carry
on a typical conv...
Michael thought he spotted the
man who'd
threatened him earlier.
I'm getting back
on the space shuttle.
No, no, no. Sorry,
sorry. Sit, please.
Let's talk about you.
Tell me about your family.
No.
They're pushy,
bossy, want to control me.
What about your family?
I'd love to meet your family.
Michael knew from experience
that this would
not turn out well.
If you like the small, why
don't you come
back for the medium?
I probably should
warn you about my mother...
Hi.
So he came up with a
solution so
simple, he'd wondered
why he'd never
told anyone it before.
I don't have a family.
I can't believe I've never
told anybody that before.
That's so sad.
Yes,it's sad. Super sad.
Shall we eat?
Michael had
started a relationship by
lying about the
existence of his family.
I think this
went really well, huh?
Maybe sometime
we can have dinner?
Could I see your house?
Michael was caught
off guard by the question.
No, no, I-I can't do that.
Okay, bye-bye.
Uh... bye.
And he vowed not to be
caught off guard again.
I didn't mean that...
So did he
invite you over, then?
Not yet, but he will.
So Michael went back to work.
Hey, who
brought in the wood...?
Gob, you can't shred this
evidence.
You'll end up in jail.
Dad told me to.
How can I say no to that face?
Get this stuff
out of here, and put
it somewhere where
Dad can't get to it.
Are you in on this, too?
No, I'm just here to go out
to lunch with your father.
The man said he's never felt
more free in his life.
I'm like a bird up there...
Ah, did you tell
him about my medal?
Medal? What for?
Oh, who knows
what they were saying?
...private citizenship and
hereby reenlist in
the armed services of the
United States of America?
If you agree with
this, say thank you."
Thank you. Wow.
I have so many
people to thank.
- Private
Ashford, step forward
It's probably because
a seal bit off his hand.
The army has taken to giving
medals for being food.
Just then...
It's so simple.
My ankle monitor only goes
off when go
out the front door.
We need balloons.
A party.
We need to throw a party...
for Buster's stupid thing.
Larry, go get some balloons.
And Michael found a way to
get Rita to his
house after all.
That's a great idea.   Honor
Buster tomorrow night.
We'll get the
whole family over to
the penthouse,
show him our support.
Well, I suppose it's
better than drinking alone.
What time?
It doesn't
matter to me. I can't
be there. I've
got a date with Rita.
Well, Mom's probably right. I
couldn't even
stand up to a seal.
I don't real
deserve a medal or a party.
No, you deserve this.
Here, take my business card.
No, no, it's
pronounced a-nal-ra-pist.
It wasn't really the
pronunciation
that bothered me.
You see, Buster, it wasn't the
seal that you
couldn't stand up to.
It was... Lucille.
Oh, I'm getting chills.
If this was a
Lifetime Moment of
Truth movie, this
would be our act break.
But it wasn't.
And later Lindsay was on the
phone with Bob Loblaw.
The thing about Tobias-- that
he's never
fulfilled me sexually.
Can you catalog
for me the various
ways you've been
promised to be fulfilled
whether or not said
promise was made explicit?
You want me to be explicit?
Yes, but I will be needing
to get off in four minutes.
Well, let's see if I can't
hit that target for you.
The next day on the
way to pick up Rita,
Michael stopped
by his house to make
sure there were no
signs of his family...
only to discover
there was nothing but.
What the hell is all this?
Oh, Gob brought
all this stuff in.
And, Mom, what is
with all the family photos?
Oh, I'm teaching Buster
to stand up for himself.
I'm surrogating your mother.
By wearing her sealskin coat?
Michael, I have tried on
everything, and
nothing seems be working.
I thought the
Donna Karan worked;
you just didn't
have the right shoes.
Look, I've got
to get rid of any
evidence of my
family and quickly--
including you guys.
Get out of here.
See, now that's how
you stand up to Mother.
Meanwhile, worried about
Steve Holt's
sexual expectations,
Maeby tried to
cancel her date.
My whole family and I now
have to go to
my grandma's house,
'cause my uncle lost his hand.
Awesome! So you and I can
party alone at your house.
Maeby was too
young to know what to do.
Ironically, in
her after-school
job as a movie
studio executive,
she'd just green-lit two films
that dealt
with the very issue.
Rock the house.
All right.
George Michael also
didn't know what to do.
If he pointed out that the two
were cousins to
drive them apart,
he might be burning the very
bridge that he one
day hoped to cross.
Michael. I'm doing
your cousin tonight.
So are you.
What?
She's your cousin, too.
Back at the penthouse, party
preparations were underway.
He's not wearing that to the
party. I've go
the exact same thing.
No, he was just analraping me.
Then Michael
barged in, and kicked us
out so he could
shred all the evidence.
Shred the evidence?
Thought he didn't
want us to do that.
He didn't want us
to get into trouble.
He's taking the heat.
He's doing that for us?
And on the night
of his date with Rita.
Who he didn't want
to bring over here.
Probably because,
let's face it, you
people haven't been
great with the others.
Well, in our defense, Mom,
we're not exactly dog people.
We have got to
start being nicer.
I'm starting right now.
Buster, the party's
not for you anymore.
It's a "Welcome Rita" party.
I know where she works. We can
pick her up and surprise her.
You're so right.
This is better
than a party for me.
Come on. Grow a pair.
You know, we need
some weather balloons
for this party and
maybe a tank of hydrogen.
You know, really
float those suckers.
Meanwhile, Michael was hiding
the evidence wherever he could
when he heard
from his brother.
Hey, friend. Gob here. We
really want you at the party.
We're really nice
now, and God, we love you.
Oh, damn it.
And the family
picked up Rita in the
only vehicle big
enough to hold them all.
Hey, excuse me, Rita.
I'm Rita.
We're here to pick
you up for Michael.
You can just go in the cabin.
Michael?
Oh, he's not here.
We're his family.
His family?
We're nice.
I'm sorry. I have to leave.
Oh, no, you can't
leave. Drive, Lindsay.
Bye!
We're doing this for Michael.
Stop her, Buster.
What am I supposed to do?
- Stop her!
- Stop yelling at me!
I'm leaving!
And that's when Buster
noticed the seal
on Rita's backpack.
Hey, talk about cathartic.
Now that's an act break.
Buster had
overcome his fear of seals.
Unfortunately, he'd done so by
knocking out
Michael's new girlfriend.
What the hell did you do?
You curious, Mom?
I can show you.
You made a mistake.
You're human...
except for the hand.
It's okay, she's alive.
And soft. Soft and alive.
All right, let's not
add that to the charges.
What do we do? She's
going to tell Michael.
And he won't
hear the good stuff.
He'll just hear
about the beating.
Wait! Maybe we can
give her a Forget-Me-Now.
Here you go, hot
dog. Take the pill.
What's a Forget-Me-Now?
They're pills that create a
sort of
temporary forgettingness.
So if somebody
finds out how you do a
trick, you just
give 'em one of these,
and they forget
the whole thing.
It's a mainstay of
the magician's toolkit,
like how clowns always  have
a rag soaked in ether.
Gob, this is Flunitrazepam.
It's a roofie.
Those are illegal.
Shut up, Mom.
Don't make me give
you another one of these.
Lindsay, help me! Three!
Back at the house,
Michael finished his
work and now late,
rushed to pick up Rita.
Moments later,
Maeby prepared to
tell Steve she
wasn't ready for romance.
Well, this
sends a mixed message.
Just as Steve showed up to
call things off
with his cousin.
You did all this for me?
Yes, well...
I'm going to go get sexy.
And Michael missed Rita.
Damn it.
Strike two.
Take it down.
We don't want anything in
this house that says "Rita."
Hi, it's
Michael. I will be coming
to the party
because I love you, too.
Okay, we need a new banner.
And that's when
Michael found Rita.
Rita...
Why am I on a
bus bench, Michael?
I get it... because I'm late.
I'm sorry, but the
rest of the night's
going to be all
about you, I promise.
Great, great.
I am going to
have to make one quick
stop. Maybe you can
just wait in the car.
It's just going to be
two seconds, I promise.
And so Michael raced up to
pay his quick
respect to Buster.
Ah, there he
is, my favorite son.
- Everybody's favorite son!
- Mr. Wonderful!
I had a great time. I wish
I could have stayed longer.
It was a great party, huh?
Tell Buster I stopped by,
please. I do
have to leave, though.
Oh, no, no. The party
is not for Buster anymore.
No, Michael, it's for you.
Take a look at
banner, Michael!
You guys did
all of this for me?
- "Family love..."
- Michael?
Everyone froze.
Michael feared he'd been
caught in a lie
about his family.
His family feared
they'd been caught by a
woman they clubbed,
drugged and left on a bench.
It was awkward.
Who's this?
Mother! Mother!
This is from army.
I have to report
for duty tomorrow.
It says by accepting this
medal, I was reenlisting.
I didn't hear them say that.
Perhaps if the sergeant had
spoken more
slowly she would have.
In acceptance of
this medal, you proudly
waive all rights
to private citizenship
and hereby
reenlist in the armed
services of the
Unites States of America.
If you agree with
is, say thank you.
Than-nk... you.
What am I going to
do? I can't go back there.
I've never been.
Who are these people?
This is my family.
No. No, I don't
like these people.
Me, you mean. She means me,
because I lied
about having a family
because I was
embarrassed by them.
And I'm ashamed of that.
I have to leave.
Strike three.
You said you
didn't have a family?
- Everody's favorite son.
- Mr. Terrible.
And her, too good for us? Huh!
Buster, you should
have finished the job.
Job? What job?
Did I say job? I meant Gob.
Buster's the one that hit
her! I just
gave her the roofie.
Roofie?
Forget-Me-Now.
You beat and drugged Rita?
Take this and love us again.
- No, Just take it!
- No, no! No, no, Gob!
Um, I'm leaving, too.
Well, no good
deed goes unpunished.
Oh, look, it's
not all bad. I-I got
Buster feeling
better about his medal.
Not anymore.
I'm getting rid of this thing.
It has caused me nothing but
pride and self-respect!
Buster went to get rid of the
medal he finally
felt he deserved,
but it was exactly when
George Sr. was
making his escape.
Farewell to you all!
But it turns out that hydrogen
is more explosive than helium.
And George
Michael came home to
find an
unconscious Steve Holt.
What have you guys been doing?
I gave him a roofie.
A girl's got to
grow up sometime.
He's your cousin.
My cousin?
I should have told
you that. Now you've
drugged him and
had your way with him.
How is that even possible?
No, George Michael,
we didn't do anything.
I just wanted
him to think we did.
Don't you see? I drugged him
not to go all
the way with him.
Well, I think
even the anti-drug
people are going
to be okay with that.
Well, let's get
his pants back on.
You took his pants off?
And Michael
tried to salvage the
remains of the
files from the car fire.
- You call the attorney?
- Yeah, I sure did,
but he's not
taking our calls because
apparently the
retainer all used up.
He took my
call. He's very good.
Yeah, that's how the
retainer got eaten up, okay?
The secretary took it all
down here on the transcript.
She's very good, too.
I'm not paying for this.
Well, what am supposed to do?
I don't know, Lindsay.
The thing you
say on page seven
looks like it could
be worth some money.
Speaking to me yet?
It's only been an hour.
You know, here, here's
what I don't understand.
What were you guys doing
with Rita in the first place?
We just wanted to do
something nice
for you, Michael,
because you do so much for us.
I guess we screwed it up.
Well I screwed it up because
I was trying to impress her
and let's face it, she's
probably too good for me.
No. What you
need to do is go to
her and ask
for another chance.
She'd be lucky to
have you, Michael.
Thanks, Gob.
Sometimes you do surprise me.
I've got one
more surprise for you.
It ain't easy being whi...
And Michael did try
again with Rita, but
this time,
determined to keep no secrets.
I want to tell you everything
if, if you're
willing to listen.
I'm a very good listener.
Great.
I'll start with the
misdemeanors and then
we're going to push right on
through to the
lighter treasons.
So, 1983, uh...
Lindsay tries to work off her
debt with Bob Loblaw.
I'm willing to debase myself.
Get a maid's uniform and
come by my house around 7:00.
There is no way
to misterpret that.
Except the one.
And a traumatized
Steve Holt needs a father.
I've made a huge mistake.
I know the feeling.
I had you.
I'm your father, Steve Holt!
I can't hide from it anymore.
I won't forget this... Dad.
I will.
Transcript: Raceman
- Synchro:
Amariss Correction: Bijaz
- Www.forom.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net