PREVIOUSLY
The murder of Margrethe Thormod,
Director of Immigration, has received...
The press is going crazy.
They want to know if it's terrorism.
Red October?
It sounds like the radical left.
No films where you see them,
no spokesmen, no manifestos.
- How is Saga doing?
- Not so good.
- Where's that gay Iranian they deported?
- Taariq Shirazi went underground.
There was a marked increase in threats
against Thormod after the deportation.
They know Margrethe was here.
It's probably best if you move on.
Get out! I'll call the cops.
I think we've found new tenants.
A woman and a son. She has it really bad.
Why did Mom die?
Are you going to stop looking for us?
They disappeared almost 8 years ago.
Am I starting to leave it behind me?
The Supreme Court acquitted me
of the murder of my mother.
EPISODE 2
I'll call you right back.
What happened?
Hey! What happened to you?
Can you hear me?
- What happened?
- I don't know. She fainted.
Hello. Are you awake?
She just fainted all of a sudden.
Can you hear me? Hello?
Are you with us?
Do you think we should
call an ambulance?
What happened?
- Sorry.
- Are you with us?
- Let's do it.
- Should we call an ambulance?
She just woke up.
Hey. Try to get up.
- Hey, are you okay?
- Sorry. Thank you.
Yeah, I'm totally fine.
I just get a little dizzy sometimes.
- Should we call someone?
- No, it's fine. Thank you.
How did it go?
- 150 kroner.
- I have this, too.
You can get at least
1000 kroner for this.
Cool.
THE BRIDGE IV
Hi.
- How's it going?
- Good.
You were damn lucky.
Did Elsa say anything?
She said she felt betrayed.
She thought it could somehow
get you to stay.
I'm going to work again.
Don't you think it would be good
to take it a little easy after this?
No, returning to work
will help me put this behind me.
No.
We know you're in contact with Taariq
Shirazi. He lives at your sister's place.
He shows up outside your apartment.
Yeah, yeah.
Are you screwing, or what?
Is he so good that it's worth
getting mixed up in a murder case -
- that could end up being
classified as terrorism?
Hi. Where are we?
He still thinks it's a good idea
to keep quiet.
You know why you're here.
Margrethe Thormod was at your club.
What was she doing there?
Who was she meeting?
If he walks out that door,
then I'll answer your questions.
- Why's that? What did I do?
- Silas, we need to know why...
As soon as he walks out that door,
I'll answer your questions.
- Jonas.
- Are you serious?
Margrethe was there to meet Taariq.
He doesn't know why.
- So he says.
- Does he know where Taariq is now?
Maybe, but he won't tell,
and that's probably understandable.
Is it? I'm all for feeling sorry for him,
but he's our primary suspect.
- Silas isn't going to say anything.
- Maybe I should have been in there.
Lillian.
Saga is being released today.
I'd like to have her here.
Isn't it a little early?
She's had a hard time.
She needs it, Lillian.
She needs to be a detective again.
You know she's damn good.
And Red October is Swedish.
I'll have a chat with Linn.
Lillian. Do you seriously mean that?
- Are you seriously thinking of using her?
- Saga?
- She's just come out of prison.
- Because she was acquitted.
Is she stable enough? You said yourself
that she had a hard time.
- Can you really afford more mistakes?
- Mistakes?
Martin's in prison.
Hanne lost a leg.
No one was charged with murdering Danish
citizens; the suspect committed suicide.
- Are you finished?
- I'm just trying to help you.
You've always had only clean hits.
There were errors both in your shooting
and when you drew your weapon.
You passed, but
the result was worse.
I couldn't practice.
- So that doesn't concern you?
- No.
Welcome back.
Can I start working now?
Lillian asked for your help
with Henrik Sabroe in Denmark.
Is that okay? You can start
by reading through the case.
- You can borrow my office for a bit.
- Great.
Yeah, I'm looking at it now.
It just confirms what I said.
It's not Red October.
- Yeah, I can write something.
- Hello.
It's no problem.
The usual rate?
Okay, good.
You'll hear from me.
Yep. Bye.
You're not ready?
I'm going to run
10 kilometers today.
- Do you have a hangover?
- No. I was beaten up when I came home.
- By that group?
- No, that girl you brought home.
Robin S.
Turns out her ex is fucking jealous.
Seriously. You need to stop
pretending to be me. Understood?
- I mean it! That was the last time.
- Yeah, I promise.
Scout's honor.
On Mom's grave.
- So no run today?
- No.
- Should I run the jacuzzi instead?
- Patrik, I have to work. See you later.
Okay. I'll just have some breakfast.
How's it really going
with your NA meetings?
- It's going okay.
- Just okay?
- No, no, it's fine. It's helping.
- I don't want any more problems.
- Do you think this will be a problem?
- It's Saga, after all.
Hey.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
- Good to see you.
Yeah...
Well, where is my desk?
We don't have fixed desks,
so you can sit where you want.
Why don't you have fixed desks?
It's something we're testing to be
more flexible and increase creativity.
Objectivity is more important
to an officer than creativity.
Yeah, but now we're trying this.
What should I do with my things?
Just take this around with you.
There.
- There you are.
- You can sit there.
- Hi. Jonas Mandrup.
- Saga Norén, Malmo Police.
Yeah, I know that.
I've heard a lot about you.
We'll have a briefing for Saga.
That isn't necessary.
I've read all the material.
Red October put out a video
on the internet today.
- They claim they didn't kill Thormod.
- I know. I saw it.
It's been impossible to track them,
but we're trying.
You questioned Silas Tuxen this morning.
Did you get anything?
He says Thormod was meeting Taariq.
But he didn't say where Taariq was,
assuming he knew.
What reason did she have
to meet with Taariq?
None. She had absolutely no reason
to be in contact with him.
We have a witness who says
that they met.
Maybe he's lying, or
maybe he just misunderstood.
She introduced herself. As far as we know,
he has no reason to lie.
Last time, you said she was cheating.
- Let me hear it.
- Hear what?
You come here with crazy allegations.
How far along are you?
For technical reasons, we can't disclose
details of the investigation.
No details. I'm asking how far
along you are, if you have suspects...
Niels. We can't disclose anything.
- Niels, you'll hear from us.
- I want to see where she was killed.
- It's still cordoned off.
- Why? Because you found something?
Did you not hear that we can't disclose
details about the investigation?
Discoveries at the crime scene
are classified as details.
Why do you want to see
where it happened?
It could be horrible.
- I need it to move on.
- She was stoned to death, Niels.
- Are you coming?
- Yeah, I'll be there in a little bit.
Yeah, hi, it's me.
No, no, no.
They know nothing.
Continue as planned.
I haven't gotten my paycheck.
- Good thing you said it.
- We agreed on the end of the week.
Take it easy.
I haven't forgotten.
Do you think it's him?
We're the sellers.
Can I see?
The money first. 1000 kroner.
Come on, man.
Let me see the passport.
The money.
Let go! Give me the passport now!
Just give him the passport, Julia.
Hey, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Let her go! Let her go, I say!
Are you okay?
What are you doing here?
Do you have any food we can have?
- And you live off of selling passports?
- Among other things.
Do you have one I can buy?
If you're blond, 55, and named Louise.
But if we get hold of one
that looks like you, then...
Okay. Thanks.
I'm going back to work.
- But take care of yourselves.
- Likewise.
Okay, make yourselves at home.
- I don't know if we can afford it.
- Don't worry.
Come.
Here's a bedroom.
There's another down there.
Bathroom.
Kitchen.
Living room.
- Can you make do out here?
- I have no choice.
Not much goes on here, but it's safe,
and that's the most important thing.
- Why is it empty?
- The previous tenants...
Didn't respect the contract.
- What kind of contract?
- It's nothing special.
I'll come back to help with furniture.
There's some in the silo we drove by.
You can just take it. It costs nothing.
We help each other here.
If anything comes up,
I live just down the road.
- Okay, see you later.
- Thanks.
It's not so bad.
It'll be fine.
Yeah?
I thought we agreed that Alexis
would move into that empty house.
We did, but the situation has changed.
- Frank's friends showed up.
- Yes, but it's not Frank's town.
It's mine.
And you know what I think about
those who question my decisions.
Here are the keys to my house.
Am I going to live at your place?
- Do you have another place to live?
- No.
I'll find my own apartment,
or a hotel in the meantime.
- Or you can just live at my place.
- You live there.
Saga, Henrik.
We know where Taariq is.
Lillian. It's me and Henrik leading
this investigation, right?
Yes, but right now I'm sending
Saga and Henrik out.
- You're prioritizing her over me.
- She's not the competition.
Equality before competence.
It's not the first time, is it?
Taariq Shirazi. Henrik Sabroe, police.
We want to talk to you.
Taariq!
Hey, stop!
- Open the door!
- Put your hands against the wall!
Put your hands against the door!
Turn around!
You called them, huh?
You called them, huh? You shit!
You shit!
Margrethe Thormod was killed by stoning.
That punishment is used in Iran.
You said if you went back
you were sentenced to death.
Look at the photo.
Margrethe Thormod was the most
responsible for your deportation.
I didn't kill her.
She tried to help me.
- With what?
- Money, a new passport, a new identity.
So first she deports you,
and then she helps you stay?
She said she had to make
bad decisions -
- and that there's something
wrong with the system.
And so she'd be able to sleep at night.
- By breaking the law?
- By being humane.
- I wasn't the first she helped.
- So you confirm the meeting at The Cave?
Yes.
- How long was she there?
- 30 minutes. Maybe a little more.
But she got a call and was very stressed.
She said she needed to leave right away.
- Who called her?
- I don't know.
- Where was she going?
- She jumped into a black car.
- What was the make? Model?
I know nothing about cars.
It was black.
- Did you see the plate number?
- No.
We'll just take a break.
It's good.
- Elderflower?
- No.
Do you own the whole town?
And all the houses?
Yeah, since 1998, when my husband
committed suicide. Up on the farm.
Frank mentioned something
about a contract.
We don't care where
you come from -
- what you believe in,
or how much money you have -
- or who you sleep with.
We're interested in only one thing.
You should be the best version
of yourselves so long as you're here.
- What does that mean?
- You should be good people.
Take care of the town, of nature -
- of the land.
Help each other -
- make a little extra effort.
Be the best version of yourselves
and hope -
- that it's enough
to be allowed to stay.
Here's the rental contract.
So...
Tell me a little about yourselves.
Is this your cell phone?
Yes.
The call Margrethe Thormod received
when she was with you -
- came from this phone.
There's a GPS program installed
that's tracking another cell phone.
Margrethe Thormod's.
I don't understand.
A program in your phone shows
where Margrethe Thormod's phone is -
- with almost exact precision.
But I don't have...
I don't understand.
I got that phone today.
- You got it today?
- Yes.
- From whom?
- From two girls.
- What are their names?
- I don't know.
Where did you meet them?
It was outside the restaurant.
They were selling a passport to a man -
- and he wanted to take it from them,
but I came out to help them...
- ...and as thanks, I got the phone.
- Just like that?
They just give you their phone
as thanks for helping?
It wasn't their phone.
I think they stole it like the passport.
- How old were they?
- Young. 14, maybe 15.
It's hard to say. One was younger.
I think they were sisters.
- And you've never seen them before?
- No.
So two young girls you'd never met.
You don't know their names.
They just tell you they're criminals,
and then give you their cell phone.
You don't believe me? Huh?
I got it from them!
I promise it's true!
You have to believe me!
There.
We've had 11 reported pickpockets
in this area in the last 14 days.
The same pattern.
Young girl acts sick, people help -
- she gets better,
and they find they've been robbed.
- Where's Taariq's restaurant?
- It's here.
- We believe him now? Huh?
- Saga.
Technicians found two sets of fingerprints
on the phone besides Taariq's.
- Small. Could be young girls'.
- Do we know who owns the phone?
- The murderer wouldn't have left tracks.
- Cameras?
They managed to avoid the cameras.
- Okay, what do we do?
- Taariq stays. We put out an APB.
- So we believe him.
- We can't take any chances.
If they stole it from our culprit, they
must be found. We'll hold Taariq.
Hello, hello!
In school, he rips paper into shreds
and sharpens pencils.
Hello, hello!
Who do we have here?
Take it easy, honey. Out.
Come on, out. Come on.
I know most of them like you -
- but my daughter is afraid of clowns.
- Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't know.
- I said it before.
It must have slipped my mind. Sorry.
Does she want a balloon animal?
No, she doesn't.
Hello, hello!
He's gone now.
Are you okay?
Shall we keep reading?
- Hey, Patrik.
- Hey.
There's a girl who doesn't
like clowns.
I know. Leonora.
The nurses told us.
- When did they say that?
- At the morning meeting.
- Where was I?
- You were next to me.
Ah, I see. Yep.
See you tomorrow.
Thanks for today.
God grant me the serenity
to accept the things -
- I cannot change -
- the courage to change the things I can -
- and the wisdom to tell the difference.
Congrats.
Isn't it great she was acquitted?
Yeah. Thanks.
- It's tea water.
- Perfect.
Thanks.
- Are you together?
- Why do you think that?
It sounded that way
when you talked about her.
It's not that simple.
- Either you're together or not.
- That's not how it is with her.
- Why not?
- Because she is who she is.
How did you meet?
I wanted her help to find the girls.
Then it became something else.
You don't know what?
The thing is, I need her more
than she needs me.
Well, that's shitty.
Yeah.
- Do you know what time it is?
- 10:07 PM.
You can't be an investigator
24 hours a day.
- But I am.
- Come on.
We'll continue tomorrow.
No, no.
Don't bring that.
- I'm going now.
- Yeah. Great. Thanks for today.
Is that okay?
- I can certainly stay.
- No, it's fine. Thanks a lot, Susanne.
What are you thinking about?
- Margrethe... Her helping Taariq.
- If he did it?
Sometimes she needed to make decisions
she didn't agree with.
Well, that's fine.
She was a good person.
She just never told me, and
we didn't have any secrets.
Do you think... Do you think
there was something she didn't tell me?
Do you mean what the police suggested?
That she was cheating?
Just...
Did she say anything to you?
- Anything that might get her killed?
- No.
And she loved you.
So much.
- Saga, what are you doing?
- Checking apartments in Malmo.
When I asked you -
- why you didn't want to live here,
you said it was because I live here.
I'm not good at living with anyone.
Okay. What about you and me?
Sometimes I'll live here, sometimes
I'll live alone, and we'll have sex.
- Only with each other?
- Do you want sex with other people?
I'm just trying to understand
what we're doing.
- I'll never be like Alice.
- I know that.
- Do you still see her?
- No.
What about the children?
Do you see them?
Yeah.
- So it has nothing to do with the drugs?
- No.
We weren't doing so great,
Alice and me.
Did you have a bad relationship?
We had some problems.
- Did you fight?
- No.
She pulled away more and more.
Got very quiet.
We didn't really talk.
But I'm glad you're here.
Yeah, you said that.
Bro, is that you?
What are you doing?
You can't be here.
Do you hear what I'm saying?
You can't be here!
Get out of here!
Go! Hello?
Get out!
- You couldn't sleep?
- No.
We thought it was
an unknown perpetrator.
If it was bad between you and Alice,
she might have gone willingly.
No, she didn't do that.
It wasn't that bad.
You didn't talk about it,
so it might have been.
She would never have taken
the children from me.
- Did Alice have any girlfriends?
- Yeah. Why?
Women trust each other
if there are relationship problems.
Yeah, but I talked to all of them
after they disappeared.
- It's not in the reports here.
- Because they didn't know anything.
- Or they didn't want to tell you.
- Alice didn't disappear willingly, Saga.
She was abducted or killed.
And I need to realize soon
that we'll never find the girls.
I'm just going to lie down again.
She sometimes doubted
if he still loved her.
Do you know if Alice talked
to others about this?
She mentioned someone from work.
- Do you know who it was?
- No, she never said.
- Man, woman?
- A man, but it was just a coworker.
She loved Henrik. She would never
take the children and just disappear.
I need to go.
You'll have to pay.
Lise said Alice talked a good deal
with a man at work.
We have a list of male employees.
I want to take a look at it.
You could have asked me
to come along with Lise.
She might not have been honest
about what Alice thought about you.
- Was she, then?
- Yes.
- Do you want to know what she said?
- Do I?
- That's what I asked.
- Yeah. What did she say?
She said you were more a policeman
than a husband.
That you were out with coworkers
and drank too much at times.
And that you let Alice take care of
the children and took her for granted.
- Also that she wasn't sure you loved her.
- Thanks, that's fine.
- But she said more.
- Yeah, but it's fine. Thanks a lot, Saga.
You're welcome.
The neighbor called it in. They found
him dead in the jacuzzi this morning.
I talked to the prosecutor
about Richard Dahlqvist.
The connection to Red October
and Margrethe Thormod is enough -
- that the case is yours.
No signs of violence.
He didn't drown.
- Heart attack?
- Unusual for a man his age and shape.
- What are you doing?
- Stay there.
I live here!
It's my house.
I'm asking you to stay there.
- Saga Norén, Malmo Police. Who are you?
- Richard Dahlqvist. I live here.
You have a twin brother.
He was probably murdered
instead of you.
- Did you feel threatened?
- No.
Were you in contact with Red October?
- It's not them. It's not them.
- Were you in contact with them?
Yeah. Some texts.
- Then we need your cell phone.
- Why?
Because of the texts.
We put things here we don't need,
but could be useful to others.
You can just take what you want.
- You're not coming?
- I'll stay here.
- See you later, then.
- Yeah. Bye.
Hey.
Did I scare you?
Frank said I could take what I want.
- Frank is my dad.
- Okay.
- Astrid.
- Christoffer.
- This was mine once.
- Is it okay if I take it?
- It wouldn't be here otherwise.
- I guess not.
- I can help you.
- Okay.
There.
- I'll get Lillian.
- Okay.
- Do you want something?
- Yes. I sat there.
Yeah, okay. Now I sit here.
It's a flexible office.
- I heard you were in Sweden.
- We'll brief you when Lillian comes.
Then we don't have to do it twice.
Okay.
- Patrik Dahlqvist.
- He worked as a hospital clown.
Richard's twin brother.
We think they were after him.
It was Richard who was
in contact with Red October.
The day before last, both brothers went
to meet them, but they didn't show.
Richard received a text
to meet alone next time.
- They were watching him, then.
- Saga, you're bleeding.
- Where is Richard now?
- Linn got a hotel room in Malmo.
- The video from Red October?
- Nothing.
Everyone leaves digital tracks.
- Not these people.
- Or you haven't found them.
My favorite police.
I've missed you.
- How are you?
- Good. What did you find?
- I've just started.
- You've had the body several hours.
You or me?
Which do you prefer?
Here.
Take this.
You'll get used to it again.
So, which is it?
You or me?
If you've just started,
you don't have much yet.
I have a pretty good theory.
He bit his tongue.
Convulsions.
Marks on his palms. Burns.
Blisters.
- He died of electric shock.
- Good.
Ida! Police! Run! Ida!
Hey! Stop, you two!
Police!
- What do we do now?
- We need to get away from here.
Lay low for a bit.
Let's go to Malmo.
Hi.
- Hi, John. Welcome.
- Thanks.
- You can sit there.
- Okay. Hi.
- Hi there.
- Jonas Mandrup. Who are you?
John Lundqvist. Technical Investigator
from Malmo. I'm going to help you a bit.
Are you? That sounds great.
Make sure you get what you need.
Start with Richard Dahlqvist's phone.
Patrik Dahlqvist died of
a strong electric shock.
And it couldn't have been
a problem with the jacuzzi?
That's not how he was found. The body
was placed like this after he died.
Anything new on the girls?
A couple colleagues found the place
they were living, but they got away.
Okay. Maybe we should try to get
more Swedes over here to help us.
We're trying to get on top of things.
Saga, Henrik, take Richard's phone
to him in Malmo.
Text Red October, asking to meet.
Put surveillance on him and go.
- We're exposing him to danger.
- Not if we do it right.
Where are the guards here?
Where the hell is he?
Come on, let's get back.
I'll call Linn.
Saga.
Saga?
Saga, what's wrong?
Saga, are you okay?
Come on, Saga. Come on. Breathe.
Just breathe. Nice and easy.
Just pull to the side.
Nice and easy.
- What's wrong?
- I don't know. I don't know!
I don't know.
Thank you.
English subtitles by S.E.
kyckling@protonmail.com