ORIGINAL WORK BY GEORGE MORIKAWA
HAJIME NO IPPO: THE FIGHTING!
I hope we get a big catch today!
-Are they biting?
-Hope they like the bait.
Alley-oop.
Mom, I'll take care of this.
You take care of our customers.
Really? Then I'll leave this to you.
Here we go!
We're so sorry.
We'll get it ready right away.
We know where the boat is.
We'll go ahead on our own.
Really? Sorry about that.
-Lugworms.
-Here!
-Tackle box.
-Now bring those out.
-Sure!
FISHING BOAT RENTAL MAKUNOUCHI
Have a good one!
‪SHOIN HIGH SCHOOL
Hey! Who wants to go see a movie?
-They're showing a good one.
-I'll go!
Yes, I want to see it, too!
Okay, that's Aikawa and Norimitsu.
Who else?
-Me.
-Okay.
We still have one more.
It doesn't matter who.
Hey, why don't you come with us,
Makunouchi-kun?
What? You mean I can go with you guys?
Don't be shy.
We all just changed classrooms
so we're all strangers.
Oh, yeah! Okay, I'd love to... Oh.
I forgot. We have a reservation
for night fishing tonight.
-What's the matter?
-Uh, I'm sorry.
We run a fishing boat business
and it's just my mother.
I have to help out again tonight.
Really? That's too bad.
Maybe next time!
Aikawa-san, let's get going!
Coming!
He turned me down the other day too.
What a buzzkill!
Oh, yeah. He was being harassed
by some scary-looking guys the other day.
Maybe he's an easy target.
They expressly invited me to come,
so why do I have to be so clumsy?
I wonder if I should be more outgoing?
But there's no way I can ignore
our family business.
-Hey, Ippo!
-Huh?
Hey!
Oh, Umezawa-kun! Please, after you!
Huh? Hey, does something smell bad?
Hey, you're right.
Something does indeed smell bad.
Huh? What could it be?
It's you! You smell like worms!
Can't you tell?
The stench of worms is all over you
because you fiddle with them every day!
I'm sorry! They're a part
of my family's business
so I can't help it.
I'm sick of it!
When you come to school,
the whole place smells like earthworms.
Actually, they're not earthworms.
They're lugworms.
Who do you think you are?!
Who asked you to correct me?!
Why do you hit me, Umezawa-kun?
Is it fun to pick on those
who are weaker than you?
If her son is this smelly,
I bet your mother smells like crap.
Damn!
Why are you looking at me like that?
Well?!
Nothing.
Why don't you show me
some guts once in a while?!
Oh, man. This is pretty gruesome.
These punks don't look so tough to me.
Who the hell are you?
Don't try to show off, moron.
What?!
You're the one who's showing off!
Ow... ouch.
Are you guys
supposed to be an electric fan?
Just because you're a little quick,
don't get carried away!
Who's getting carried away? You or me?
Uh, well, um...
-You'll pay for this!
-Damn it!
Amazing.
Hey! Wake up!
Come on, wake up!
What?
Big Guy, he's awake!
-Hey, are you all right?
-Uh, yes.
Where am I?
This your first time in a boxing gym?
Boxing gym?
Yeah. I brought you here
because we're equipped
with first aid supplies.
Thank you for your help!
I really, really appreciate it!
That's enough thanks.
If you feel better, hurry on home.
I hate bastards who prey on the weak,
but I am disgusted
with those who just get bullied
and don't even try to fight back!
I bet your mother smells like crap.
I'm sorry to have troubled you.
-Wait a minute!
-Huh?
Man! You're frustrated enough to cry.
Hold on. I'll let you try something fun.
All right. Pretend this is that bastard
and take a swing at him!
What? But it doesn't look like...
Shut up and do it!
It'll make you feel better.
Yes, sir!
If you insist, uh...
Does it go like this?
There. Ow!
If you're pissed off,
use everything you got on it!
Yes, sir!
-What're you shouting about, Big Guy?
-Shut up. It's nothing.
Everything I've got.
That's it. That's the spirit.
See? Doesn't he
look like he's in pain now?
Try to step into it harder.
Step into it, sir?
The moment you step into it,
lock it in with your hip.
Also, try to twist your shoulder inward.
Right!
Step in, hip...
Shoulder!
Okay.
Huh?
That feels great!
I did it like you told me,
and it swung up that high!
Did you see it? Did you?!
It really does feel great!
It's so invigorating!
Ow.
-Get over here!
-Ow!
Did you see his knuckles?
The skin was peeling off.
You mean like a typical hard puncher?
Him? Couldn't be.
HAJIME NO IPPO: THE FIGHTING!
BANDAGES
Sandbags are hard, aren't they?
All done.
What the heck are you doing?!
You're a lot stronger than you look, kid.
-Do you play any kind of sport?
-Not really.
I'm too busy helping out at home
to have any time to be on a team.
We rent out fishing boats, you see,
so my mornings are full too.
Anyway, you seem to have a better feel
for punches than I expected.
Why don't you try
to flatten those suckers next time?
No way, I couldn't do that!
I'd get knocked out for sure!
You won't know that unless you try!
An ordinary person wouldn't be
standing after a punch like that one.
But I've never been in a fist fight.
Besides, like you already saw,
I'm always the one who gets bullied.
If you don't do anything about it,
everything will stay the same.
Huh?
Are you okay with that?
It's not that I'm okay with it...
Oops. It's time. Got to go.
What? Where are you going?
Roadwork!
"World Title KO Collection"?
Watch them. You'll feel better.
Return them whenever you want!
WORLD TITLE KO COLLECTION VOL. 1
WORLD TITLE KO COLLECTION VOL. 2
Well, everyone,
let me escort you to the boat.
I'm home! Sorry I'm late.
Welcome home. Oh? What happened to you?
-Where did you get all those injuries?
-Uh, it's nothing.
Hey, am I making you too busy
at home to make friends?
Are you being bullied?
Not at all! I'll help you right away.
Hey, those have ice in them.
Are you going to carry all of them?
Come on, everyone. It's this way!
Please watch your feet. The boat rocks.
I heard the tide is good today.
You'll get a big catch, for sure!
I'm sorry to make you
help me all the time.
But you're still only in high school.
You can leave the business to me
and do whatever you want to do, okay?
Uh, right.
Have a nice trip!
I'm sorry.
I'm the one who should apologize.
I bet your mother smells like crap.
If I was stronger...
FISHING BOAT RENTAL MAKUNOUCHI
WORLD TITLE KO COLLECTION VOL. 1
GLORIOUS MEN!
STORIES OF WORLD CHAMPIONS
INCREDIBLE COLLECTION OF KO SCENES
They're so strong.
I wonder what it feels like?
I wonder how it feels to be so strong?
I'm late!
BOXING FAN MONTHLY
TAKAMURA'S UNSTOPPABLE
SEVEN CONSECUTIVE VICTORIES
Makunouchi!
Whoa.
-Makunouchi!
-Yes, sir!
Low kick!
Dragon Screw!
Ouch.
The Dragon's too dangerous!
Okay, I'll give you a head lock
instead of a Figure Four leg lock!
They're wrestling and fighting again.
I don't like that stuff.
Why do guys like sweaty,
stinky stuff like that so much?
Boxing is kind of dark and depressing too.
Yeah, no kidding.
You... shouldn't make fun of boxing!
-Huh?
-Back Drop!
He's not off the floor!
Uh, I got carried away.
Uh, good morning!
Oh, it's you! Did you watch the videos?
I did! Over and over!
Thank you so much, Takamura-san.
How do you know my name?
-From this.
-Oh.
That's amazing.
Imagine being the rookie king of the pros.
No wonder you're so strong.
That's so cool!
Ha! Of course I'm cool,
but I'm not giving out
autographs right now.
I'll sign it for you at the gym.
Do you think I can do boxing too?
I'd like to learn boxing too.
Huh?
Well, uh, I thought
I'd like to become a boxer too.
Boxing is no sport for a wimp like you!
But I could get you
a "Workout for Dieting" or something.
Would that be good?
Well, uh, that's not what I...
That's not what I meant.
I want to become a professional boxer.
I want to be strong and fight in matches!
Takamura-san,
you said I had a feel for it, so...
-Don't mock boxing.
-What?
I don't appreciate your decision to
become a boxer on a whim like it's easy!
It's not a whim!
I gave it serious thought!
It's no world where a bullied mincemeat
like you could survive!
I gave it serious thought.
I seriously decided to start boxing.
I'm determined!
I want to be strong like you,
Takamura-san!
I want to be a new person!
Takamura-san, what does it mean
to be strong?
How does it feel to be strong?
All right.
Come with me!
So, you want to be like me, do you?
Watch closely!
What?
Come over here.
-Do what I just did.
-You mean me?
If you manage to do this,
I'll teach you some boxing.
Can I pull something like that off?
The jab.
The most basic skill in boxing
and one that a boxer must acquire first.
The jab measures distance, acts as a wall...
and creates a window for attack.
Quickly and sharply!
I won't give up. I'll never give up!
I'll achieve my dream.
I'll become a new person no matter what!
Next time, "Fruits of Labor."