ORIGINAL WORK BY GEORGE MORIKAWA
HAJIME NO IPPO: THE FIGHTING!
Yikes! Makunouchi can't stand up!
The blow was that powerful!
Will this decide the match?!
This guy is too much for me!
No, it isn't me!
It's having an effect!
His last attack used up
his final shred of strength!
But he still managed to
squeeze out that much power.
Yeah!
Even Miyata-kun fought way past his limit!
I can't cop out
just because my right fist hurts!
How can I expect to defeat this guy
if I'm that weak?!
I have to do better!
Kid!
I can't possibly beat this guy
if I'm that weak!
He's up! Makunouchi has risen to his feet!
VICTORY OR DEFEAT
You bastard! You should've stayed down.
I was naïve to believe
I could fight fully without my right fist!
There's no way
I could defeat him like that!
I cannot afford to lose.
I will win! I'll beat you down
as many times as it takes!
I don't care if it costs me my right fist!
I'm fighting against an incredible boxer!
I'm going to fight until I'm satisfied!
Now, the match is about to resume.
Mashiba slowly walks
in front of Makunouchi.
Now they face off!
I'll finish you!
Kid!
It's not enough!
It'd take more than this
to make Mashiba-san fall!
Two reps from the right! That stupid kid...
He's placed the last glimmer of hope
on his right fist!
It's still not enough!
He keels over!
Makunouchi's three great consecutive hits
makes Mashiba's tall frame capsize!
Mashiba's legs are buckling!
His knees could touch canvas
at any moment!
Will he fall?!
It... It'll take more
than that to knock me down!
I'm starting to lose feeling
in my right fist.
I must go now while he's still reeling
from the earlier damage!
No! If he takes
a punch in the face right now,
there's no way he'll withstand it!
I can't lose.
I can't afford to lose!
Good! Anyway, stay in there!
I can't afford to... I can't afford to lose!
Break it up! Step back!
Mashiba! Let go of him!
This guy has no intention of letting go!
Then I can also play dirty!
I'm not about to lose!
Why, you...
Neither is compromising!
Both boxers display great tenacity!
Who will fall first?!
Ippo! Keep punching!
You're getting to him!
Stick to it, Mashiba!
Boxing isn't all fists!
Shake him off, Makunouchi!
I can't... afford to...
Oh, my! Is Mashiba losing his grip?!
Just a little more!
It's coming undone!
Mashiba's clinch is
gradually coming undone!
Get...
off...
of...
me!
He's off!
Mashiba has released his grip!
Go, kid! It's your chance!
Pour your heart
and soul into your punches!
Watch out, Mashiba! Look down!
Dammit!
Ryo!
He's down!
Mashiba falls!
He did it!
Mashiba truly persevered,
but he finally falls for the first time!
And in all likelihood,
this will be a reversal KO!
Don't bother counting.
There's no way he'll get up!
Don't stand up.
My right fist has gone dead.
I can't punch anymore!
My strength is gone.
So, don't get up! Please don't get up!
Hurry!
Hurry up and count!
Stay back!
I don't want to... lose!
Mashiba exhausted his strength!
He literally sank into the canvas!
I did it.
I won!
I did it!
The match is over!
And at this very moment,
the featherweight class Rookie King
of the Eastern Japan Rookie Tournament
has been determined!
-His name is Ippo Makunouchi!
-Yagi-san, you're crushing me!
I can't believe he took Eastern Japan!
He did great!
That took a lot of guts.
Reckless idiot.
Who knows what damage
you did to your right fist?
Right now, it's in one ear
and out the other.
Anyway, you've done a good job so far.
Mashiba!
No! It's not over yet!
Come on, you bastard!
Stop it, Mashiba! It's over!
-Shut up!
-Come on...
It's not over yet!
There's no way I'd lose
to someone like him!
Uh, excuse me...
How should I say it?
Thank you for the fight.
Let's go, Mashiba.
Damn it!
Mashiba! You did great!
Yeah, you've got guts!
Next time, win by KO!
Come back to Korakuen Hall someday!
Shut up!
He certainly was a fearsome opponent.
Yes.
When I knocked him down at the end,
I was convinced
he would get to his feet again.
So I started chanting, "Don't get up!"
The count felt like it took forever.
I was the one standing over him,
but I was scared to death.
But in the meantime,
you beat the guy you were so afraid of.
For you're the Rookie King
of Eastern Japan!
Chief...
Now, go on and salute them.
Right!
Makunouchi! Nice fight!
You always reverse the match!
That's what's great about you!
Don't make us so nervous!
HAJIME NO IPPO: THE FIGHTING!
The Eastern Japan
Rookie Championship Tournament
was fought in a total of 11 classes.
The rookie champions
from all classes are here tonight!
The fight for each class
was full of invigorating
matches worthy of fresh fighters.
And now, the awards ceremony!
This is nerve-wracking.
I had no idea there was
a ceremony following the final match.
And next, the award given to the most
impressive boxer of the tournament,
the MVP Rookie Award goes to...
Makunouchi in the featherweight class!
Huh? What?
You mean...
I'm the MVP Rookie of the Year?
Uh... Thanks.
MEDICAL ROOM ENTRANCE
4TH FLOOR EMERGENCY EXIT
KEEP DOOR SHUT AT ALL TIMES
Ryo...
Look what you did to yourself for me.
It must have hurt all this time.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry!
That last punch...
That last punch... really hurt.
The guy definitely had a crushed fist,
but he still delivered
a horrific punch with it.
I was so sure this was my chance
to climb up to the top,
but it's all over now.
Ryo...
Ryo? Maybe boxing isn't...
Maybe you should...
I have to start over.
After all, the best thing
about boxing is that it's all fair.
This world is pretty comfortable.
It's too good to quit.
That's true.
When you get better,
you can try for it again.
I never expected Ippo to make MVP!
I can't believe it!
Really. We didn't predict that at all.
What's your damage, loudmouth?
My dark horse came in first!
Remember?! We bet on it before!
We bet on who would win, Ippo or Mashiba!
I was the only one who bet on Ippo, so...
Right, Takamura-san?
You took notes, right?!
Hey, isn't that a little much?!
That should shake him out
of his alcohol stupor!
Alcohol?
What are those guys doing?
Ozuma-san...
Kobashi-san...
Hayami-san...
Mashiba-san...
They all did themselves proud.
Miyata-kun...
In the end, I didn't get to fight you.
But I'm sure the way
I fought today would make you proud.
So I'm the Rookie of
the Year for Eastern Japan.
EASTERN JAPAN
ROOKIE CHAMPIONSHIP TOURNAMENT
KO TIME: 3R, 2 MINUTES, 13 SECONDS
IPPO MAKUNOUCHI
EASTERN JAPAN ROOKIE CHAMPIONSHIP
TOURNAMENT FEATHERWEIGHT WINNER!!
NEW EASTERN JAPAN ROOKIE
OF THE YEAR AWARDED MVP ROOKIE AWARD!!
KAWAHARA BOXING GYM
MONTHLY BOXING FAN
MVP GOES TO FEATHERWEIGHT IPPO MAKUNOUCHI!
IPPO MAKUNOUCHI (KAMOGAWA GYM)
CONQUERS THE FEATHERWEIGHT CLASS
AND SECURES RECORD OF
6 MATCHES, 6 WINS, AND 6 KOS
SHOIN HIGH SCHOOL
Ooh, he's in here!
He's in here! Let's see...
He conquered featherweight
with his dynamite punches!
The other time he was in here,
it was a tiny write-up.
But now that he's rookie champ,
he gets the star treatment!
Oh! Hey, Ippo!
Oh, Umezawa-kun!
I haven't seen you
since the end of last semester.
Yeah. Anyway, congratulations...
Rookie Champion of Eastern Japan.
I was moved!
What? You came to watch?!
Of course! I've been there
for all your matches.
-Yeah!
-Thank you!
I'm totally looking forward
to the All-Japan Tournament.
We'll definitely be there to root for you!
I hate to say this when
you have such high hopes for me,
but it looks like I'll have to withdraw
from the All-Japan.
Withdraw?! How come?
I fractured my right fist.
It'll take two months to heal.
The All-Japan is in February.
My fist will just be healing up
by then, so...
I see.
Besides, it'll take a while to recover
from that last match.
Chief said I should focus on
running for the time being.
Which means, for the time being,
we won't get to see you fight.
-I'm sorry.
-Hey, don't sweat it!
Tell us when you get your next match.
We may be working full-time by then,
but we'll be there to cheer you on.
Sure!
For you, this is the last semester
of your high school career.
Oh, yeah.
My high school days are almost over.
Umezawa-kun and the others
will go find work,
and I'm sure everyone else
has decided what they want to be.
I told my teacher I was going to
keep boxing, but I wonder.
That's why, whether you are
going to seek employment
or go on to college,
I would like you to fight hard
for your goal.
That is all.
My goal?
The Eastern Japan was my goal.
I don't know when my next match will be.
I need to find a new goal.
I wonder how
Mashiba's little sister is doing?
Please stop badmouthing my brother.
I haven't been to that bakery since.
I couldn't bring myself to tell her
that I was his opponent.
She probably came to the match,
so she must have been surprised.
There's no way
she feels positive towards me.
I have to give her an apology!
All right, here goes!
But how do I apologize without sounding
like I'm making excuses?
What should I do? I can't turn back now.
At any rate, I have to go!
Well, take care.
I will.
Welcome...
Um, hello.
Huh?
Please, come in.
Uh, sure!
I mean, uh...
We have some freshly baked pastries.
What? Uh, no... That girl!
I mean, I would like some yakisoba buns.
Pardon?
YAMANAKA BAKERY
Thank you, come again.
Do you need anything else?
Um, about that girl who was just here...
When will she be working next?
What? Oh, do you mean Kumi-chan?
Actually... today was
Kumi-chan's last day here.
What? Her last day?
She's going to be a secretary
at her brother's place of work.
She was a good girl
and the customers really liked her,
so I'm sorry to see her go.
That can't be.
For some reason, it doesn't taste as good,
even though it's
the same old yakisoba bun.
I guess I'll never get to see her again.
Although she didn't do it directly,
she completely broke my heart.
So, that was the last "welcome."
NANIWA BOXING GROUP
Is Mashiba losing his grip?!
Mashiba's clinch is
gradually coming undone!
Those are good uppercuts.
I can't wait. I'm so excited!
Finally.
I've finally found someone
I can fight fair and square.
I can't wait!
I can't wait for
the All-Japan Rookie Championship!
I'm waiting for you, Makunouchi!
KAMOGAWA BOXING GYM
The smash. A punch thrown
in an upward slant
that uses a well-trained body
like a giant spring.
It is powerful enough to knock down
an opponent with a single blow.
It is a weapon
that was prepared by someone
who's been looking forward
to fighting with me.
I'd love to fight him
if only I didn't have an injured fist!
I love boxing too!
Next time, "Rocky of Naniwa."