ORIGINAL WORK BY GEORGE MORIKAWA
HAJIME NO IPPO: THE FIGHTING!
You dummy! Be the turtle!
Keep your guard up!
I'm a turtle!
Oh, you idiot! Ippo, up! Get up!
Is that all he's got?
What is this?
He hit me in the middle and...
I don't know what happened next!
TEARS OF JOY
So, he has a little willpower.
I'm sure Takamura-san
brought him here for a reason.
Why did you lower your guard?
I got hit in the middle
and stopped thinking.
It's count Eight!
Go on! Keep both hands up!
Hey, how come they're using the ring?
Didn't they know we're up for sparring?
Don't ask me.
I heard Takamura-san brought
in some weirdo off the street.
Some weirdo?
There isn't anybody in this world weirder
than Takamura-san.
That's true.
Listen, don't forget. You're a turtle!
No matter what, keep your guard up
'til the end of this round and persevere!
Yes, sir!
No matter what,
don't let your guard down, got it?!
Yes, sir!
Good job! Keep your guard up!
Who the heck is that?
Is that an amateur?
Why are you getting excited
over an amateur?
We were scheduled to spar, you know.
Shut up! I reserved the ring!
King Unreasonable is back.
I think the Chief is behind it.
What, really?
So, he's blindly following instructions.
They have another thing coming!
Oh, you idiot!
Now for the inevitable nap.
Miyata knows boxing all too well.
Well, shall we begin?
You fool!
Didn't I tell you
not to let your guard down?!
But...
I'm way out of his league.
So, is it over?
You idiot! Don't you
want to become a boxer?!
Or is that all there was
to your commitment?!
What happened to the perseverance
that drove you to grab ten leaves?!
That's right. I decided...
I'm going to be a boxer!
Hey, he got up again.
Yeah. I guess he can take a beating.
Glad you're up!
Your dream would be history
if you didn't show your stuff first!
Anyway, be a turtle!
Keep it up
until the end of the first round!
Fight!
The next one is the third knock-down.
It's all over now.
Dummy! You got caught too easily!
Whoa! Awesome blow on blow!
-That's got to hurt.
-Get away! Use your feet! Your feet!
My feet?
What the heck is that?!
Can't you do it with a little more style?
But...
The moment he lets his guard down,
he's through!
I'll never let my guard down!
I have to keep going!
Well, at least he's hanging in there.
He's not letting his guard down.
One more minute till
the end of the first round.
Miyata is underestimating Ippo
and only using his left hand.
As long as he doesn't use his right,
Ippo can tough it out somehow!
So, why can't he knock him down
with that huge barrage?
I guess Miyata's punches
are weaker than I thought.
Damn!
Oh, crap!
It's over.
What the...?!
-You're kidding!
-He took it!
My God.
-He took Miyata's right.
-And he's still standing!
Damn.
I'm saved!
After all that, he managed
to make it through Round One.
And without any experience.
It's hard to believe.
Great job hanging in there, kid.
He's amazing.
Did you see him?
He keeps punching me in the stomach,
going for my face!
It's amazing!
I can't believe he's my age
and can do all that!
It's all in how you look at it.
By the way, how come
you can take a beating like that?
Don't tell me it's because
you took punches from bullies every day!
Maybe that's it.
I know these are practice gloves,
but they sure hurt.
My head is still spinning.
Not enough to stop you from talking.
Oh, yeah! I made a huge discovery!
It hurts, but it sure doesn't hurt!
What's that supposed to mean?
I can't explain it.
When I was bullied,
the physical pain didn't hurt as much as
my self-disappointment.
The emotional pain was totally unbearable...
But now, I feel like
I can get back on my feet
no matter how many times I get hit.
I wonder if he got a blow
to the wrong place.
So, have your feet been affected?
Can you still move them normally?
Uh, yes, I think so.
Good. You'll start taking
the offensive in the second round.
What? But I've never tried to hit anyone.
I wouldn't know what to do!
You idiot! I already taught you how!
Oh, the jab!
Right, now listen. You can't catch Miyata
by scrambling around.
Slide toward him, and corner him.
Right!
You already know your range, right?
Like grabbing those leaves!
Uh, yes!
-Use your right if you can, too!
-Right!
Miyata, what are you doing?
It's already the second round.
Are you holding back?
Don't let that amateur
play with you too much.
He isn't even trying to punch you.
He's like a sandbag.
You don't need to tell me.
This is humiliating.
Still, Takamura-san is his cornerman.
Who knows what he's telling him?
Oh, he's taken a fighting pose.
Let's see. Elbows tight at the sides,
fists at eye level.
What's he mumbling about?
Hey, he's starting to look like a boxer.
It's just a bluff.
We'll see about that.
I'm still too far away to grab a leaf.
Not yet.
Just a little more.
Let's see what he's got.
He's in range!
Whoa, he jabbed!
What a jab!
He's fast! I thought he was an amateur!
-The klutz ain't too shabby!
-He's pretty fast too.
Those are some good jabs,
but this won't last forever.
-Now! Right jab!
-Right!
What the heck?
Can't he do anything but jab?
Ow!
What's with that wipeout?!
I taught you the straight punch, remember?
-Huh?
-Did you forget?
Think back to when you first punched
a sandbag in this gym!
Um, I think it was important
to step in deep and twist the hip.
The shoulder is supposed
to turn inward, just like jabbing...
He's doing it again.
I'll admit you've got pretty sharp jabs,
but I'm afraid I can't let you hit me.
Miyata's good.
Takamura-san looks amazed.
Technically, Miyata ranks
over non-licensed boxers.
Maybe he's afraid of
seeing someone better than him.
He's getting short of breath.
We'll see who can endure longer.
My arms are getting heavy!
His arms are probably getting tired.
My arms are dead heavy!
Just a little longer.
My turn.
My arms may be dead heavy,
but I can't stop now!
Now!
Foot! Hip!
Shoulder!
-What the...?!
-His guard!
-It's knocked away!
-He's wide open!
Go!
One more punch!
HAJIME NO IPPO: THE FIGHTING!
-His guard!
-He's wide open!
Go!
One more punch!
-So close!
-If only that got in!
-His punches are pretty strong.
-This guy isn't bad!
-I would've done it.
-That was so close.
You're pretty good
with both your left and right fists.
Thanks.
Don't get pleased with yourself!
Recite everything I've taught you so far.
Um, the left jab, guard,
sliding footwork, and the right straight.
Good! We're going to use
all of those in the next round.
Keep your guard up, approach him,
and hit left, then right!
Understand?!
Uh, right! Left, then right.
It's amazing he made it
to the third round.
Which will prove superior?
The rookie's right punch
or Miyata's skill?
This actually might be something to see!
It's not going to be that easy.
Ippo may appear to be on higher ground,
but he hasn't hit Miyata once!
The right straight punch
at the end of Round Two
was the chance of a lifetime.
It's a shame he didn't pull it off.
Miyata won't make the same mistake again.
What's worse is he's all fired up now.
He'll be giving it his all
in the next round.
It would have been interesting
if the amateur's right had hit Miyata.
He may not be as powerful as we thought.
Maybe he's afraid
of the kid's right punch.
They're clueless.
If they think boxing is about power,
they're gravely mistaken.
What's important is the right timing
and skill to pinpoint
an opponent's weakness.
Keep my guard up, left then right!
Left, right!
This time he's doing the one-two!
I'm impressed!
Hey, he's good!
Hard to believe he's an amateur.
The great Miyata is in defensive mode.
Miyata's being way too quiet.
Is he waiting for something?
You definitely have incredible power.
But remember this. In boxing you can also...
knock down your opponent like this!
So, he was going for the chin.
When you take one on the chin,
your brain sloshes about your skull,
causing temporary functional impairment.
What is this?
But what a brilliantly aimed punch!
It's probably over now.
He got us. What a guy!
He may be fully conscious,
but his body won't do what he tells it.
He won't be able to stand up.
Hey, do what I tell you to!
-He got up!
-You got to be kidding!
How come a total amateur can get up
after getting his chin crushed?!
How are you standing?
Left, right.
Ippo!
That did it.
Ippo, get up!
Impossible!
I won't let it end!
I made a commitment to become a boxer!
One more fall and it's over.
There isn't much time left.
Hang in there, Ippo!
Right!
-Amazing.
-His punches are still going strong.
Ugh, I can't bear to watch.
His face is getting deformed.
How can he keep punching
in that condition?
He shouldn't be able to stand!
The only thing keeping him going
is his determination to become a boxer.
That's how he's withstanding
Miyata's punches.
I won't fall down. I won't!
I'm going to be a new person!
I'm going to be a boxer!
What an amazing kid!
He forced down his spastic legs
and fought back!
Why? Why aren't you falling down?
This is insulting!
It's like everything I know about boxing
is being debunked!
Left... right.
Fall down!
I did it!
You bastard! Down! Fall down!
Left... right... left!
-Right!
-You're pissing me off!
Look out, Ippo!
Don't do it! He'll throw a counterpunch!
I'm going to be a boxer.
Hey, Ippo!
Hey, Ippo! Ippo!
Oh, man. He's out cold.
Someone bring a bucket of water!
-Uh, right!
-I'll come with you!
Hey, old man! Were you watching?
Old man?
The kid has a lot of grit.
Gritty boxers aren't in style nowadays.
However, the greats, like Harata,
Ebihara, Obao, and Washima...
Those famous boxers got up again and
again every time they were knocked down.
And every time they did, we were inspired.
Old man! So that's where you're hiding.
You watched it till the very end, I hope!
So, you think he isn't cut out for it?
Whose eyes are blind? Mine or yours?!
That's some sloppy mess
you brought into my gym, boy.
I haven't seen many guys who'd put up
such a fight
in a mere sparring session.
Tell him to come here
every day starting tomorrow!
I'll make a boxer out of him.
He sure gave you
a hard time though, Miyata.
And you used a counterpunch on him.
Don't you think that's bullying, much?
I wasn't bullying anybody.
He was wearing the same 16-ounce gloves.
But look at these arms that blocked
those punches.
Boxing has just become
incredibly interesting to me.
Hey, are you awake now?
Oh, yeah. I lost.
I lost without getting even one punch in.
You really showed a lot of grit!
-Nice fight!
-You were amazing!
Keep it up! You'll be coming here
starting tomorrow, right?
The name's Kimura. Nice to meet you.
I'm Aoki.
You've got good punches,
but your defense needs work.
I'll put you through
the mill starting tomorrow.
You're in no position to talk
about someone else's defense!
That's mean. I was all ready
to train the new guy!
Huh? New guy?
The Chief says you passed.
He wants you here starting tomorrow.
That's great news, kid!
Hey, guys! I'll re-introduce him.
This is our newest member,
Ippo Makunouchi!
Passed? I'm in?
-Hey, say something.
-Oh, right!
How do you do? I'm Ippo Makunouchi.
Starting today, I've...
I've been accepted into this gym...
Into this gym as an apprentice.
I'm pleased to make your acquaintance!
FISHING BOAT RENTAL MAKUNOUCHI
Step work. As soon as
you step in, you step back.
Soon as you go to the right,
jump to the left.
The sounds of footwork in the ring
are ever-changing and brilliant.
Carefully observe the out-boxer's weapon.
I'm sure I'll be able to
see Miyata-kun's shadow!
Next time, "Shadow Boxing"!