ORIGINAL WORK BY GEORGE MORIKAWA
HAJIME NO IPPO: THE FIGHTING!
Manabu Tamura-kun.
SHOIN HIGH SCHOOL
SENIOR YEAR GRADUATION CEREMONY
Same as above.
Congratulations.
Thank you, sir.
SHOIN HIGH SCHOOL
SENIOR YEAR GRADUATION CEREMONY
Satoshi Nishimura-kun.
Same as above.
Congratulations.
Thank you, sir!
Ippo Makunouchi-kun.
Same as above.
Congratulations.
Thank you, sir!
Way to go, our hero!
Makunouchi!
-Makunouchi!
-Congratulations!
He certainly is popular.
Apparently his last match
received rave reviews.
Yes.
So, he's going to continue boxing
while helping with the family business?
I was concerned for a time
when he chose boxing
over continuing education,
so I gave him a word of advice
at the counseling session.
Really? What did you say?
I said, "You're still young,
so do what you want to do!"
Is that so? He certainly opened my eyes.
College isn't all there is to life,
after all.
THE CONTINUING JOURNEY
Well, I'll be getting home now.
I'll come with you.
We have night fishing, right?
I'll be okay by myself.
Your friends are waiting for you.
At least for today,
forget about home and take it easy.
I will. Thanks, Mom.
Congratulations, Ippo.
Ippo!
Your juniors want a photo with you.
What? I'm not good at stuff like that.
Oh, come on, come on.
They say they're fans of yours.
Fans? So, where are they?
Look behind you.
Yo!
Sir! I saw your last match!
Sir! It deeply moved me!
Sir! It made me weep!
Sir! Please let us have a photo with you!
Eh? Yes. If you would like.
All right, I'm going to take it!
Line up!
Don't drag your feet!
Ready?!
Sir!
I'll root for you twice as hard!
Take the championship.
Sir!
Thank you so much for your support.
Makunouchi-sempai!
Please take a photo with us too.
Me, too!
Makunouchi-sempai!
Please join us for a picture!
Please, All-Japan Rookie of the Year!
Okay, form a single line!
What? You're kidding.
You popular guy, you!
You lucky devil.
What a predicament.
To them, you're the sempai or classmate
they have bragging rights to.
Come on, hero.
Won't you give them a little service?
Service?
Is that everyone?
Then perhaps I'll get a shot
with him as well...
Hey! The next shot is the last one.
Oh, we have to get in on it, too.
All right, line up!
You're lining up?
So, who's going to take it?
Cheese.
What do you mean, no good at it?
You posed like a bandit at the end.
Still...
He really doesn't look
a thing like the guy in the ring.
Like even I could take him easy.
I was so mean to him.
Huh?
-What's wrong?
-Huh? Well, you know...
So, you're a professional boxer.
I'm jealous!
What? Really?
Well, you know, me and the guys
have to start jobs this spring
that we don't even like.
I'm sorry.
Hey, don't apologize.
It'll make it harder for us
to do our thing.
I'm sorry.
But still, it sure is cool to be
able to keep doing what you like!
Yeah.
Well, I guess this is
where we say goodbye.
Yeah. I'm going this way.
Well, see you later!
Umezawa-kun?
Say...
What is it?
Actually, there's something
I have to say to you.
Listen...
I...
Tell him that you're sorry for everything!
Tell him that you think he's amazing!
Oh! Is it about my next match?
My right fist isn't healed yet,
so I don't know when it is yet.
That's not it!
I'll contact you once I know when it is.
That's not it.
I'll be there for sure! You have my word!
Make sure to contact me!
I'll be there to root
for you no matter what!
After all, you're
our shining star of hope!
I can't wait to cheer you on!
Umezawa-kun...
Give it your best, Ippo!
Don't lose to anyone!
Umezawa-kun.
They say that Sendo-san
has already resumed training,
and both Ozuma-san and Hayami-san
have made their comebacks with KO's.
Little by little,
they're coming after my position.
I'd love to relax...
but it will probably get harsher
than I can imagine from now on.
I stopped by your house
after my own grad ceremony.
What is it?
Uh, no... Is your foot feeling any better?
You didn't let me see you
when I came to visit.
Um, well, I...
You went to my house?! What for?
I'm going to be leaving Japan for a while,
so I wanted to say bye.
What?
I'm going to be doing
the rounds in Korea and Thailand.
I thought I'd get a look
at the tough guys over there,
and, of course, do some fighting too.
That's amazing! So, how long
will you be there?
The All-Japan Rookie of the Year, huh?
It didn't take long for me
to get so far behind.
I'll be there until I catch up.
I have no time to relax.
I'm going to do it.
I'm going to get to it!
From now on, my life is boxing!
HAJIME NO IPPO: THE FIGHTING!
KAMOGAWA BOXING GYM
APRIL
MASARU AOKI VS ARMAN GARCIA
TATSUYA KIMURA VS SHINHIRO KANZAKI
HISHOU JAPAN MIDDLEWEIGHT CHAMP MAMORU
TAKAMURA VS THAILAND #2 BONCHAI CHUWATANA
Their matches are coming up soon.
I hope everybody wins.
I'm back.
Now, does everybody have one?
You need to have this stamped by tomorrow,
and don't forget your entry fees.
Yes, sir.
There's been a flood
of new applicants lately.
Our gym's fantastic four,
Takamura-kun, Kimura-kun,
Aoki-kun, and you, Ippo-kun,
have been a huge draw.
Thanks to you guys,
we'll be able to order a new sandbag.
So, it's been two years
since I joined the gym.
I'm the most recent applicant
to join and continue boxing,
but this new batch looks hopeful,
and maybe I'll finally get a junior to...
Sorry, but could you move?
Uh, sure.
I always wanted to
try punching one of these.
-Don't poke around.
-Right.
I guess my presence
doesn't command authority.
Ugh, I'm starving!
Count your blessings.
Starvation diets are murder
when you work in a ramen place.
That's the Lightweight Aoki-san!
Kimura-san's with him.
Wow, they're talking about
starvation diets.
Yeah, that's amazing.
They got changed!
Let's watch them for a bit.
It's nonchalant, but that type
of action sure fits the role.
They sure do seem like pros.
Holy cow!
I can't see his hands!
Does that mean Takamura-san
is even faster?
Of course. He's the champion, dummy!
Actually, the new Rookie of the Year,
has incredible punches.
I came to this gym because
I want to be just like Makunouchi-san.
The Rookie Championship
got me totally wired!
When it comes to destructive power,
Takamura-san is superior.
They're in a different weight class.
I know that!
Damn, they're noisy.
Hey, so you are here, Ippo!
Huh?
You were right beside me
and I never even noticed?!
I thought you were a newbie like us!
You look like another person in the ring.
It's Takamura-san!
In the flesh! Is this for real?!
He's so dignified!
I wonder if I can get his autograph?
Keep the noise down,
you annoying chatterboxes!
Uh, Takamura-san!
Chill!
Don't get anywhere near this guy
when he's dieting!
Go home! You can't be a pro
if you drool around
like girly groupies
waiting for an autograph!
I'm serious, you know.
I have a lot of confidence in myself.
And my endurance is second to none!
Yeah!
Then why don't we put that to the test?
It's quite simple.
We're merely going to see
if you can keep up with
the amount of roadwork we normally do.
I know I'm the next champion,
but I would be thrilled.
-Oh?
-This sounds like fun.
Shall we get this started?
All right, follow me!
Yes, sir!
Is it okay to start
with that out of nowhere?
Humph. It'll do them good to have
a taste of severity right off the bat.
It will thin out the losers,
leaving only those with guts.
But still...
I'll supervise them.
Yikes.
Those guys never cut any slack.
Hey, are you okay?
You should rest a little.
Hey, come on. You have to rest!
It's not an actual test, so don't worry.
You're free to join,
and you can slowly
get used to doing roadwork.
Take a deep breath.
Well, once you feel better,
try to catch up.
I'm used to it, so I'm numb,
but the world of boxing is really tough.
Only one?!
Humph! They were all mouth.
But I didn't get their entry fees yet!
What the heck, right?
Guys without the guts
wouldn't last long anyway.
Where are you going?
Uh, I... have to be getting home.
I'll come back tomorrow.
Think he'll come back?
He won't be back.
And I was going to
make a fighter out of him, too.
What's up, Ippo?
It's just that I was looking forward
to getting lots of juniors to coach.
Sorry to hear it.
Look at that, Ippo. One's coming this way.
Good show!
He's got a lot of gumption.
Undoubtedly, he wants to join the gym
because of my influence.
Okay, I think I'll take a look at the guy.
No. I'll make a boxer out of him.
What are you talking about?!
He came to this gym to be like me!
I'll look after him!
Now, dive...
...into my waiting arms!
Well, got to go practice.
But you can't! He ran the whole course!
Okay, so you look after him.
We're busy.
For crying out loud!
You did a great job.
Looks like he got himself a great junior.
Yeah.
-Is Barf-michi still in the shower?
-Barf-michi?
His name is Naomichi Yamada.
He's 16, high school second year!
He's a barfing Naomichi, so "Barf-michi."
Good name, right?
Sure.
No sports experience, huh?
With that height, he's a welterweight.
We can get more out of him.
I'll leave a change of clothes here,
along with the stuff in your pockets.
Is this a pass holder?
-Hey, what's up with you?!
-What's up?
Aha, so he's hiding something!
Is it a picture of a girl?
Without further ado...
I see. Barf-michi is an Ippo fan.
I envy you, Ippo.
KOURAKUEN HALL
When the main event features
Takamura-san, it sure gets packed.
HISHOU JAPAN MIDDLEWEIGHT CHAMP MAMORU
TAKAMURA VS THAILAND #2 BONCHAI CHUWATANA
Do your best.
I hope all three of you win.
So you're here to cheer them on too,
Yamada-kun?
What a coincidence to meet like this.
What? It's not a coincidence?
I thought you would come here,
so I watched for you.
Since morning?
-How are you feeling?
-Great.
You'll see! We'll all score by KO.
What's that skulking behind you?
Uh, well, Yamada-kun also
wanted to offer some encouragement.
Go on.
Go on, encourage them!
Give...
it...
your...
best.
Well, do your best!
That's no good.
You have to encourage them properly.
They're all nervous right now.
Yeah.
Oh, well.
Anyway, Yamada-kun,
this is your first time backstage, right?
Uh, yes.
Once you walk through this corridor
and up those stairs,
you're in the stadium.
When you go through here,
it's so nerve-wracking.
Do you see the blotches here and there?
Can you tell what they're from?
No.
They're glove marks.
Once you've made it this far,
there's no going back.
You tell yourself over
and over to calm down.
With little thumps, like this.
But you don't have
to be nervous right now!
-Oh, Ippo-kun.
-Fujii-san!
The Kamogawa Gym
has a busy day ahead of them, huh?
I'm sure everyone will win.
I see. Oh, I'm glad I ran into you.
I'll introduce you to my surprise guest.
I don't need an introduction.
How's your right fist, Makunouchi-kun?
You know about me?
You're the hopeful who's
been blowing away the competition.
Of course I know about you.
Ippo-kun, this is...
I know.
How could I not know?
This is the Featherweight Champion
of Japan...
Eiji Date-san!
KAMOGAWA BOXING GYM
Champion.
What every boxer
in his class strives to be.
A peak that only one person can stand on.
Faster than anyone.
More skilled than anyone.
Stronger than anyone.
It is unimaginable to fight such a person.
But an actual meeting
with such a person in the ring
is no longer so far in the distant future!
Next time, "The Champ and I."