You gonna stay around a while?
Since I left for America...
all I thought about was coming back here.
When I saw Naples from the airplane,
I got a hard-on.
What do you expect? It's home.
I don't know anymore.
Even the San Gennaro cathedral.
I went to pray for my father.
There were hamburger wrappers everywhere.
I don't think it's litter that's got you
turned around.
There's a woman.
So, go home to her.
You did the duties of a son.
She is the don's wife.
Soprano?
- He doesn't know.
- You fucking her?
No.
I'm not even sure that she knows.
I never even kissed her.
Good, so you stay away.
No harm done.
I don't know if I can.
- I love her.
- You fucking crazy?
All the shit I pulled in my life,
I never fucked the boss's wife.
You know why?
Do you know why?
Stop the rhetorical questions.
Because I know he would
kill me if he found out.
And they always find out
everything, the bosses.
Hello?
Hold on.
I have to take this,
my lawyer.
The only way you could have her
is if you killed the man.
- I know this.
- Eh, so? Don't be an idiot.