- THIS IS OUR LIVES,
AND I WANT THE PASSION BACK.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT
TRYING TO COOK HER DINNER.
- I'LL DO ANYTHING
TO HELP YOU, MY FRIEND.
- OH, MY GOD.
- DINNER IS SERVED.
- I LOVE IT.
- IT'S GOOD?
- MM-HMM.
- I WAS NOT EXPECTING
THIS NIGHT TO END LIKE THIS.
- I THINK WE DID GOOD, BRO.
- THANK YOU.
- THANKS, BABE.
[Icona Pop's I Love It]
- ♪ I DON'T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT ♪
♪ I DON'T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT ♪
♪ I DON'T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I DON'T CARE ♪
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- BABY'S SLEEPING.
I KIND OF WANT TO GO
ON VACATION.
- JUST ME AND YOU?
- ME, YOU, ROGER, AND JENNI.
- OH, GOD.
HE WANTS TO GO
TO, LIKE, PROBLEM CLASSES.
- NO, IT'S A VACATION.
- LIKE COUPLES RETREAT.
- NO, JIONNI.
IT'S LIKE--LIKE A NICE,
ROMANTIC GETAWAY.
WE ALREADY BOOKED THE TRIP.
- [chuckles]
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
- A DUDE RANCH!
- A WHO?
- DUDE RANCH.
- A DUDE RANCH?
- YEAH.
WHAT'S A DUDE RANCH?
I MEAN, IT SOUNDS LIKE
IT'S GONNA BE
A BUNCH OF DUDES IN A RANCH.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT A DUDE RANCH IS.
LIKE BROKEBACK MOUNTAIN?
- YEAH.
- IT'S A BUNCH OF GAYS.
- JIONNI!
THERE'S NOTHING AGAINST GAYS.
- I DON'T HAVE NOTHING
AGAINST GAYS.
BUT YOU BOOKED--
YOU BOOKED A PRIVATE VACATION
THAT'S SUPPOSED TO BE ROMANTIC
AT A GAY PLACE.
- IT'S NOT--OH, MY GOD.
IT HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH BEING GAY, OKAY?
YEE-HAW!
[both laugh]
- WHY DO YOU HAVE,
LIKE, A DONKEY ACCENT?
- WHY DO YOU KEEP
CALLING ME A DONKEY?
- 'CAUSE YOU DO DONKEY
IMPRESSIONS FOR EVERYTHING.
- NO, I DON'T.
- NO? OKAY.
OH, MY GOD.
[laughs]
[horn honking]
- YO!
- HOWDY, PARTNERS.
- JENNI AND ROGER LOAD UP.
IT'S TIME TO GO ON A ROAD TRIP
TO THE DUDE RANCH.
YEE-HAW.
- YEE-HAW!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- LOOK AT ROGER'S ASS.
HIS ASS IS OUT.
- EEW! ROGER!
- SPREAD IT!
- WHO AM I DATING?
- [laughs]
EW!
- OH, MY GOD.
- GOOD TIMES.
- ♪ WELL, I AIN'T EVER ♪
- OH, THERE IT IS.
PINEGROVE.
- RANCH AND FAMILY RESORT.
- WHOO!
- SON OF A BITCH, WE'RE HERE.
- WE MADE IT.
- YAH, LITTLE DOGGIES.
- DUDE RANCH. WHOO!
- WHOO! WHOO! WHOO! WHOO!
- OH, THEY'RE LIKE CABINS.
ALL RIGHT,
EVERYONE GET IN CHARACTER.
- OH, YEAH.
- I DON'T HAVE MY THING.
- I GOT MY [bleep] KICKING BOOTS
ON RIGHT NOW.
- YOU DO?
- THE DUDE RANCH.
IT'S VERY NATURE-Y.
CAMPING KIND OF THING.
- "NATURE-Y."
- NATURE-Y.
- WHY ARE WE WEARING
COWBOY STUFF?
- I DON'T KNOW. [bleep].
- [laughs]
- 'CAUSE THERE'S HORSES HERE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN WHY ARE WE?
- THERE'S HORSES
IN TOMS RIVER TOO.
- SO WE GET TO PINEGROVE,
AND IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
IT'S LIKE, CAMP-LIKE.
- YEAH.
- BUT LIKE, FUN, RESORT-ISH.
- IT'S LIKE LODGE-ISH.
I THOUGHT IT WAS GONNA BE
MORE, LIKE...
- SURVIVAL.
- YEAH, YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN.
- WELCOME TO THE LOVE PADS.
- OH!
- THE LOVE SHACK.
BUNK BEDS.
[chuckles]
- THIS IS NICE.
- IS THIS REAL?
- THIS IS GREAT.
MAKE THIS WORK.
- WE TOTALLY CAN'T HAVE SEX.
- WELCOME TO MY WORLD.
[chuckles]
- "HI, Y'ALL.
WELCOME TO THE RANCH.
DROP YOUR BAGS OFF
AND MEET US AT THE BARN."
- LET'S DO IT.
SO WE'RE HEADED OUT NOW TO START
OUR ACTIVITIES FOR THE DAY.
I FORGOT MY CHAPSTICK.
- YOU HAVE THE KEY?
- YEAH.
AND THIS IS A PERFECT
OPPORTUNITY
FOR ME TO SNEAK BACK IN
AND PUT THE SNAKE IN THE TOILET.
- WE GOT A WEEKEND
FULL OF PRANKS.
WE GOTTA USE 'EM.
- OH, YEAH.
RIGHT, LET'S DO IT.
- IT'S GORGEOUS OUT HERE.
- HI.
- ALL RIGHT.
- NICE.
- WELCOME, GUYS.
- HOWDY.
- HELLO.
- WE WALK TO THE BARN, AND WE
ARE GREETED BY JESSICA AND MIKE.
- NICE PEOPLE.
THEY'RE NOT, LIKE, HILLBILLY
LIKE I THOUGHT PEOPLE
WOULD BE, KIND OF.
- YOU KNOW WHAT'S GOOD ABOUT US?
WE'RE VERSATILE.
WE'RE ABLE TO GO FROM GUIDETTE--
- WE'RE LIKE A CHAMELEON.
- YEAH, TO COUNTRY--
[snaps] LIKE THAT.
- YEAH.
- ALL RIGHT, HAVE YOU GUYS
EVER MILKED A PIG BEFORE?
- MILKED A PIG?
- NO.
- AGAIN, I CAN'T SAY
THAT I HAVEN'T,
BUT I NEVER CALLED HER
THE NEXT DAY.
- CAN YOU MILK A PIG?
I NEVER HEARD OF THAT.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
A PIG HAD NIPPLES TO MILK,
SO I--THIS IS GONNA BE
THE FIRST FOR ME.
- THE FIRST THING WE'RE GONNA DO
IS WE GOTTA CATCH 'EM.
- THAT'S GONNA BE--
- I'M ALL ABOUT IT.
- LET'S GO.
- GO CHASE SOME PIGS.
- 13 SUMMERS IN SEASIDE,
I'VE CAUGHT A FEW PIGS.
- YEAH, YOU CAUGHT
A BUNCH OF 'EM.
THAT'S ALL THAT
COMES OUT OF SEASIDE.
- I MET YOU IN SEASIDE!
[goats bleating, pigs squealing]
LET'S GO, YOU LITTLE PIGGY.
- ROGER, PLEASE BE CAREFUL.
- BABE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
BABE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- COME HERE. COME HERE!
LITTLE SON OF A BITCH.
- [screams]
- GET OVER HERE,
YOU LITTLE RASCAL!
- OH, MY GOD,
THAT GOAT'S GOING AFTER YOU!
- GET AWAY.
- RUN, PIGGY, RUN!
- ROGER!
JIONNI!
- CORNER HIM, CORNER HIM.
- AH!
- UH-OH, HE BIT IT.
MAN DOWN.
- JIONNI!
- GET IN THERE. GET IN THERE,
NICOLE, GET IN THERE.
- RUN AWAY!
[laughs]
OH, MY GOD.
JIONNI!
- [laughs] OH, DOWN AGAIN.
- OH, MY GOD,
IS THAT THEIR BALLS?
JESUS [bleep].
- THOSE PIGS ARE UN-GETTABLE.
- YEAH, LEAVE THEM ALONE.
- I FEEL LIKE, YOU KNOW,
IT WAS A REAL
GAME OF CHESS
WITH THE PIGS AND JIONNI,
AND I FEEL LIKE A PIG
WON THAT GAME OF CHESS.
- YEAH, GUYS, THAT'S JUST
A JOKE WE PLAY ON CITY SLICKERS.
YOU CAN'T MILK A PIG.
- [laughs]
- I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU CAN'T MILK A PIG.
I'M FROM EAST HANOVER,
NEW JERSEY,
SO THE JOKE'S ON US.
- YOU GUYS READY
TO GO MILK A COW?
- YEAH, BUDDY.
- YEAH.
- I'LL GET IN THERE AND GIVE
THIS LITTLE GIRL A WHIRL.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GOTTA MOVE
THAT LEG A LITTLE BIT, GIRL.
- ROGER, SHE LIKES YOU.
- I FEEL LIKE I HAVE A GOD-GIVEN
TALENT TO MILK UDDERS.
YOU KNOW, I PRACTICE IT
ROUTINELY ON JENNI.
SHE SEEMS TO REALLY HATE IT,
BUT I STILL FEEL LIKE I HAVE
AN UNFAIR ADVANTAGE HERE.
- THERE YOU GO, BABE.
TRY AND GET THE OTHER ONES.
- [laughs]
- [gasps]
- WHOA!
- [bleep]!
- OH, MY GOD!
- EWW!
- [bleep] AWESOME.
IT WAS LIKE A PORNO.
YOU SHOULD'VE BEEN LIKE...
- [laughs]
- BUT YOU WERE LIKE, "EWW!"
LIKE EVERY GIRL DOES.
- YOU ARE NEVER HAVING SEX
WITH ME EVER AGAIN.
[laughter]
- NICOLE, YOU SHOWERING FIRST?
- YES.
I HOPE THERE'S NO SPIDERS.
I WILL CRY IF I FIND A SPIDER.
[water running]
[screams]
- WHAT DID YOU DO?
WHAT DID YOU DO?
- WELCOME TO THE DUDE RANCH!
- WHO PUT THE SNAKE--
- LOOK IN THE TOILET.
- [screams]
WHAT THE [bleep]?
- I ALMOST TOOK A BIG [bleep]
ON A SNAKE.
LIKE, WHO WOULDA GOT
THAT SNAKE OUT? NOT ME.
- IMAGINE IF NICOLE
[bleep] ON IT.
- I WAS ABOUT TO!
[laughs]
- EW. YOU DON'T GOTTA TELL US.
- [laughs]
- EE!
- GET OUT.
- EW, THERE'S TOILET-
- [chuckles]
- [screams]
- ANNOYING.
- WELCOME TO THE DUDE RANCH.
THAT WAS A REAL SCREAM.
- THAT WAS REAL TERROR.
THAT WASN'T JUST A FAKE SCREAM.
- BE RIGHT BACK.
- ROGE, GREAT PRANK.
YO, YO, YO.
PUT SOMETHING IN THE BAG.
- WHERE'S NICOLE'S BAG?
- UH, RIGHT THERE.
PUT A SPIDER IN IT TOO.
- WHICH ONE, THIS ONE? THIS ONE?
- YEAH.
- SHE'S COMING.
- OH, MAN, THESE GIRLS
ARE SO GULLIBLE.
I FEEL LIKE WE COULD SCARE 'EM
WITH A BUTTER KNIFE.
- PA-POW!
- YEAH. [laughs]
- ROGE, WE SHOULD CUT OUR JEANS
LIKE REAL WESTERNS.
- [screams]
WHAT IS THAT?
- OH, MY GOD!
- WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS TO ME?
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
- WHAT IS THAT?
- I DIDN'T DO IT.
- DUDE RANCH PRANK WARS.
JERKS.
- [bleep].
- DAMN IT.
- YOU'RE GETTING HIT
LEFT AND RIGHT.
I CAN'T IMAGINE
WHAT'S UP NEXT FOR ME.
- I'M SCARED.
I HOPE YOU'RE DOING
SOME [bleep] TO HER.
- [bleep] YOU.
- WHAT'D I EVER DO TO YOU,
YOU [bleep]?
- POOP SMELL'S COMING IN
STRONG NOW.
WE'RE GETTING CLOSE.
- IT'S TIME TO GO
DOWN TO THE STABLES
BECAUSE WE'RE GONNA BE
RIDING HORSES,
AND I HATE HORSES.
WELL, I DON'T HATE HORSES.
IT'S LIKE, I'M TINY,
AND THE HORSE COULD
DEFINITELY TAKE ME OUT.
I DON'T WANT TO DIE.
MY LIFE IS GOOD RIGHT NOW.
- WHOA, WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
- WHAT?
- OH, THAT'S A BIG SPIDER.
- WHAT IS IT?
- OH, MY GOD!
- DON'T, DON'T, DON'T, DON'T...
- ROGER!
- I DO NOT PLAY AROUND
WITH SPIDERS.
THAT'S MY BIGGEST FEAR.
WHEN I SEE A SPIDER
AND I'M AROUND ROGER,
WHO I KNOW IS GONNA PICK IT UP,
I'M OUT.
ROGER!
- DON'T DO IT TO ME.
DON'T YOU [bleep] DARE.
I'LL BREAK UP WITH YOU.
WE WILL NO LONGER BE ENGAGED.
- I'LL KICK YOUR BALL SACK IN.
- PLEASE DO.
- DOES HE HAVE IT IN HIS HAND?
- STOP. STOP.
I'M GOING, I'M GOING.
OH, MY GOD,
THESE JEANS ARE TOO TIGHT.
- WHOO! WHOO! [screams]
- WATCH IT!
- [screaming]
MOMMY!
- STOP! DON'T YOU DARE!
- I WANT MY MOM!
I WANT MY MOMMY!
- STOP! STOP!
I'M GONNA PUNCH YOU IN THE FACE,
I'M GONNA PUNCH YOU IN THE FACE!
STOP!
- [laughs]
- UGH!
[laughter]
I HATE ALL OF YOU!
I'M REALLY GETTING OVER
YOUR PRANKS.
HONESTLY.
- PA-POW!
- JESUS!
- I DON'T KNOW
IF I WANT TO DO THIS NOW.
- COME ON.
- BUT DO WE GO ON TRAILS, OR DO
WE JUST GO IN CIRCLES IN HERE?
- WE GO ON TRAILS.
- ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
COME ON IN.
- WELCOME BACK.
- I'M SCARED.
- THERE'S NOTHING
TO BE SCARED OF.
- I'M NERVOUS.
- ONE FOOT.
- I'M CONQUERING
A FEAR RIGHT NOW.
- ONE, TWO, THREE,
LIKE YOU'RE GETTING ON A BIKE.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
SWING YOUR LEG OVER.
- OH...
- THERE YOU GO.
OKAY.
- I'M NERVOUS.
- IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
- IS THERE A SEATBELT?
- NO. NO SEATBELT.
- UH-OH, STOP, STOP, STOP, STOP.
- PULL BACK. PULL BACK.
- I DON'T WANT THIS,
I DON'T WANT THIS.
- WHOA, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I THINK HE'S JUST THIRSTY.
- HE'S PISSED, HE'S PISSED.
- NO, HE'S NOT. HE'S JUST
TRYING TO GET SOME WATER.
- NO, NO, NO, STOP, STOP.
[horse whinnies]
MY [bleep] HORSE
WOULDN'T LISTEN TO ME.
THERE IS NOTHING LIKE
GETTING ON SOMETHING
AND IT BASICALLY LOOKS AT YOU
AND GOES, "[bleep] YOU."
- OH, YEAH, DEFINITELY.
YOU HAD A HORSE THAT IS YOU.
- YEAH, IT LITERALLY
SHOOK ITS HEAD AND WAS LIKE,
"I'M THIRSTY,
I'M GOING TO GET WATER."
- I DO WHAT I WANT.
- YEAH.
- THAT'S YOU.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
- HEY, MIKE. DO THEY [bleep]
AND WALK AT THE SAME TIME?
- YES, THEY CAN [bleep]
AND WALK AT THE SAME TIME.
- WOW, I CAN DO THAT TOO.
- OVER HERE, OVER HERE.
WHEW!
- GOOD GIRL.
- I NEED A XANAX.
WE DEFINITELY GOTTA
HAVE A VICTORY DRINK.
- NICOLE KILLED IT.
I WAS BEYOND PROUD OF HER.
I MEAN, SHE WAS REALLY NERVOUS
AND CONQUERED HER FEAR
RIGHT THEN AND THERE.
- WE'RE ALMOST THERE, GUYS.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- THAT WAS SO SWEET.
- I WAS PROUD OF YOU.
- YOU DIDN'T TELL ME THAT.
- YEAH--
NO, YOU JUST WEREN'T LISTENING.
- THAT'S NOT TRUE.
- OKAY.
- THAT'S SO SWEET.
THINK I PEED MY PANTS.
- [laughs]
DANG.
THAT'S A LONG RIDE BACK.
- TELL ME IF THERE'S
AN OUTHOUSE.
- IT'S IN THE WOODS.
- YOU PEE IN THE WOODS?
- YEAH, YEAH.
- JOHN WAYNE DIDN'T
HAVE NO OUTHOUSE.
- [bleep] ME.
I DON'T WANT TO BE PEEING AND A
[bleep] SPIDER JUST JUMPS ON ME.
I MEAN, WE'VE DONE THIS BEFORE.
IT'S JUST SCARY BECAUSE
THERE'S CREATURES EVERYWHERE.
JENNI, I'M SCARED. JENNI.
- THERE'S NO SPIDERS.
I CHECKED IT OUT.
- [squealing]
JENNI. JENNI.
WHERE DO I GO?
I DON'T WANT TO PEE ON MYSELF.
I'M SCARED.
THERE'S SO MANY BUGS.
AS I'M PEEING, I LOOK DOWN
AND THERE'S HUGE WORMS
UNDERNEATH ME.
FAT WORMS LIKE THIS,
MOVING UNDER MY VAGINA.
- ALL RIGHT, WELL...
- THAT ONE'S FOR THE BOOKS.
WHAT IF I HAD TO POOP?
- [laughs]
- BABE, YOU WANT TO FISH?
- NO. FINISH WHAT?
- FISH.
- OH, FISH, YEAH.
OH, JIONNI'S UP IN THAT
SON OF A BITCH.
HE WENT WITHOUT ME.
- YEAH.
- SO WE'RE AT THE LAKE,
AND THE LAKE HAS FISH IN IT.
SO WE GOTTA GO FISHING.
WHY NOT?
WHAT DO YOU GET FOR BAIT?
- WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
- NOTHING YET.
I'M SURE THIS IS GONNA BE
AN ONGOING CHALLENGE
BETWEEN MY LITTLE BUDDY AND I.
- THE BASS MASTERS.
- SEE WHO CAN CATCH
THE MOST FISH.
- ALL RIGHT, HOLD IT DOWN.
BRING IT BACK, AND LET IT GO.
KEEP THE BUTTON DOWN.
OKAY, KEEP IT DOWN.
NOW, LET GO
WHEN YOU GET TO THE TOP.
HEADS UP!
[laughs]
OH, GOD.
- YOU CROSSED LINES.
- OKAY, GIMME THIS.
- HOLD MY POLE. HOLD IT.
- IT'S ON HER, IT'S ON HER.
- HOLD MY POLE.
- JIONNI, IT'S ON THE LADY.
[laughing]
- HOLD MY POLE.
- MY BAD.
IT'S HER FIRST TIME.
- I'M SO SORRY.
- IT'S HER FIRST TIME.
- [laughs] OH, MY GOD.
- SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- I'M SO SORRY
IT GOT IN YOUR HAIR.
I'M NEW.
I DON'T WANNA FISH ANYMORE
BECAUSE I ALMOST TOOK
SOMEBODY'S EYE OUT, SO...
- NICOLE, I NEED LIVE BAIT.
- OKAY, WHAT DO YOU
WANT ME TO FIND?
- I WANT YOU TO GO
BACK IN THE WOODS,
THIS IS YOUR MISSION.
YOU HEAR ME?
CAN YOU DO THIS?
- WHAT DO I GET?
- I'LL GIVE YOU
SO MUCH KISSING TONIGHT.
THIS IS YOUR MISSION.
CAN YOU ACCOMPLISH THIS?
- YES, SIR.
- THIS IS NICOLE'S MISSION.
- DON'T LET ME DOWN.
- YES, SIR.
- BABY, WE NEED WORMS.
- [groans]
I DON'T LIKE WORMS.
- COME ON, MAN.
GIMME A WHOLE BIG ONE.
- AH! STOP [bleep] WIGGLING.
STOP WIGGLING.
THIS IS THE GREATER GOOD.
THE GREATER GOOD. NO. NO. NO.
NO. NO.
[shuddering]
I DON'T LIKE
SLITHERING THINGS.
I DON'T LIKE WHERE I CAN'T TELL
THE HEAD APART FROM THE BOTTOM.
GROSS! IT'S JUST GROSS.
JUST GET IT ON.
- WAIT. I'VE GOT A BITE.
- [whispering]
IT'S THE TINIEST WORM EVER,
JENNI.
- I JUST CAUGHT ONE.
- YEAH, ME TOO.
- OH, SNAP.
I GOT CHEESE.
IT'S THE ONLY THING I FOUND.
- I'M NOT GETTING
[bleep] MICE.
CHEESE. WHAT AM I GONNA
DO WITH CHEESE?
- I GOT YOU SOMETHING.
- YOU GOT ME CHEESE.
- AND I GOT YOU CHEESE
AND I ALMOST GOT CAUGHT
AND, LIKE, MURDERED.
I STOLE SOMEBODY'S CHEESE.
IF WE WERE EVER STRANDED
IN THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE,
WE WOULD SURVIVE.
- HERE WE GO, BABY.
HERE WE GO.
- HEY, WE GOT ANOTHER ONE, BABY.
WE GOT ANOTHER ONE.
[laughs]
MAN, THAT SIDE OF THE WOODS
JUST SUCKS.
HEY, JENNI, YOU BETTER
HOPE YOU DON'T GET HUNGRY.
WHOA! BASS, BABY!
LARGEMOUTH!
- HOW'S THIS FEEL,
MOTHER[bleep]?
- AT THE END OF THE DAY,
YOU'RE STILL SHORT.
- WHO CARES?
AT LEAST I GET SOME.
- I'M GONNA KICK YOU
RIGHT IN THE FACE, JIONNI.
- THIS FISHING CONTEST
IS HEATING UP RIGHT NOW.
- IT'S GETTING BAD.
JENNI, THIS IS WHAT
A FISH LOOKS LIKE!
- WE'RE EATING TONIGHT,
DON'T WORRY.
- MOTHER[bleep]!
- GOT ANOTHER ONE.
- [bleep].
- WHAT?
- HE GOT ONE.
- HE'S GOT TWO!
- JIONNI HAS THREE!
- THE GIRLS ARE
ABOUT TO GO AT IT.
- YEAH, THEY'RE, LIKE,
SMACK-TALKING.
- WE GOT A SNAKE,
A TURTLE, AND A FISH.
- THEY'RE GOING AT IT
RIGHT NOW.
OH, MAN, THEY WERE
CRACKING ME UP.
- OH! I THINK THAT'S A LITTLE
BIGGER THAN YOURS, BUDDY!
GUESS WHO'S
EATING GOOD TONIGHT!
- NO.
- YEAH.
- [laughs]
- NO.
- OKAY.
- [laughs]
- THERE'S MORE
SNOOKI AND JWOWWON THE WAY.
- AND IT CONTINUES NOW.
- OH, HOW ROMANTIC.
- STARVING?
- THIS IS ROMANTIC.
- I'M GONNA MAKE LOVE TO YOU
BY THE CAMPFIRE, BABE, TONIGHT.
- AWW.
- SO TONIGHT
WE ARE GOING TO DINNER.
AND I FEEL LIKE WE CAME HERE
TO BE ROMANTIC,
SO WHY NOT, YOU KNOW, AT LEAST--
- ONE NIGHT.
- DO ONE NIGHT OF ROMANCE.
- NO PRANKS.
- BE CUTE. YEAH, NO PRANKS.
JUST BE IN LOVE.
- JUST ROMANCE.
- I HAD AN AWESOME,
AWESOME TIME TODAY.
- MM-HMM.
- ME TOO.
- NICOLE, DID YOU END UP
LIKING YOUR HORSE RIDE?
- YEAH.
AT FIRST I WAS LIKE,
"[bleep] THIS [bleep]."
- YEAH, YOU WERE MOST NERVOUS
GOING INTO IT.
- I KNOW, AND THEN I BECAME
THE MOST NERVOUS.
- THEN WHEN I WAS ON IT
I WAS LIKE,
"OH, MY GOD, THIS IS BEAUTIFUL."
- I WAS IMPRESSED
WITH YOUR FISHING SKILLS, MAN.
I'LL BE HONEST WITH YOU.
- MINE?
- YEAH, I WAS LIKE, "DAMN,
THE KID OVER THERE
IS [bleep] NAILING 'EM.
AND YOU HAD A FAKE-ASS WORM.
- NICOLE WAS CRACKING ME UP.
- WHY?
- SHE HIT SOME GIRL
IN THE HEAD CASTING IT.
- NO WAY.
- YEAH.
- I WAS, LIKE,
FIVE FEET AWAY FROM HER.
- I FELT SO BAD.
- SHE DUCKED, SHE SAT DOWN,
AND I HAD TO TAKE THE POLE.
- [laughs]
- AND GO GET IT.
- EMBARRASSING.
- DUDE, WE MUST'VE FISHED
FOR, LIKE, THREE HOURS.
- FOCUS RIGHT NOW IS ON DINNER,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
IN THE BACK OF MY HEAD, I GOT
PRANK WAR NUMBER SIX GOING ON.
BECAUSE WE ARE GONNA GET THEM
AT THE END OF DINNER.
WE'RE DEFINITELY GONNA
PRANK THEM ONE MORE TIME.
- IT'S TIME. IT'S SHOW TIME.
- PRANK OF ALL PRANKS.
WANT TO GO SIT
OVER BY THE CAMPFIRE
FOR A LITTLE BIT,
MAYBE HAVE SOME S'MORES?
- LET'S DO THIS.
- YAY.
- LET'S DO IT.
- WHOO!
- THIS IS AN ART. TO NOT BURN
IT. YEAH, YOU'RE GONNA BURN IT.
- ROGER SAID DON'T BURN IT.
SHE SHOVED IT
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE--
- I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING.
[Roger and Jionni laugh]
- DOES THAT LOOK BURNT?
- YES.
- NO. LOOKIT.
- I GOTTA PEE, MAN.
YOU GOTTA PEE?
- YEAH.
- MY FACE IS BURNING.
GO AND LOOK FOR ALIENS.
- I'LL PROBE YOU.
- [screams, giggles]
STOP.
GO AWAY.
- I'M A LITTLE DRUNK.
WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM ME?
WHOA.
MY ASS AND BACK HURTS
ON THIS THING.
- ARE YOU AND ROGER
GONNA DO IT?
- NO, I'M NOT GONNA DO IT.
YOU'RE IN THE BED NEXT TO ME.
I DON'T GET OFF KNOWING
THAT THERE'S PEOPLE WATCHING,
AND YOU WATCH.
- NO, YOU SICKO.
- SO DO YOU WANT ME TO HAVE SEX
RIGHT NEXT TO YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
- NO, I'M JUST ASKING.
- WHAT WOULD YOU DO?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- WOULD YOU WATCH,
TURN AROUND, OR LEAVE?
- PROBABLY JUST GO TO SLEEP.
- THERE'S NO WAY.
PEOPLE NEXT DOOR COULDN'T EVEN--
Roger and Jionni: ARGH!
[girls scream]
- [screaming]
STOP IT!
[laughter]
- I HATE YOU.
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
I MEAN, THERE HAD TO BE
ONE PRANK.
THIS DINNER CAN'T JUST
GO ROMANTICALLY.
- I LOVE THAT WE GOT
EACH OTHER'S BACK.
I GO AFTER YOUR GIRL TO KILL,
AND YOU GO AFTER MY GIRL.
- WHY DID YOU GO THAT WAY?
[laughter]
- SO MEAN!
- THE GIRLS WERE TERRIFIED.
I DON'T CARE WHAT THEY SAY.
- THEY WERE BOTH PRETTY GOOD.
THAT WAS--THAT WAS GOOD.
ROGER AND I NAILED THIS. WE--
IT WAS THE BEST PRANK SO FAR.
- BED TIME.
- ALL RIGHT,
IT'S OUR TURN TONIGHT, BABE.
BABE.
- DO YOU SEE THIS?
- YES.
- IT'S OUR TURN.
[both laugh]
- YOU GUYS ARE SO CUTE.
- [groans]
- OH, GOD, NO, NO, NO, NO.
I REALLY--I'M TOO FULL.
STOP. STOP. DON'T EVEN--
I'LL THROW UP ON YOU.
BABE.
BABE, NO, I'M PANICKING.
- WAAH!
[laughter]
- [laughing]
- AAH! I CAN'T BREATHE!
I'M GONNA THROW UP!
- AH! AH... AH...
- [laughs]
- WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
- OH, MAN.
- BECAUSE I CAN'T BREATHE.
- YOU STUCK YOUR KNEE UP
WHILE I WAS SHOVING HIS--
- BECAUSE IT WAS A REACTION.
I'M SORRY MY KNEES
HURT YOUR BALLS,
BUT YOU HURT MY STOMACH.
- IT'S BLUE BALLS
ONE WAY OR THE OTHER.
- YEAH.
- 400 POUNDS.
I'M SO SORRY, BABE.
YOU LOOK CUTE.
EASY ACCESS.
- YOU WOULD THINK THAT.
- I'LL PROBABLY HEAR IT
IN 15 MINUTES.
- M'KAY.
- TEN.
- I'M JUST GOING TO BED
LIKE THIS, 'CAUSE YOU'RE WARM.
- [screams]
[laughter]
WHO DID THAT?
- OH, MY GOD!
- JIONNI.
- ALL RIGHT, FIRST OFF,
DON'T BLAME ME.
SECOND, DON'T SCREAM.
[imitates scream]
I'VE NEVER SEEN YOUR MOUTH
OPEN THAT WIDE.
[laughter]
- PAYBACK'S A BITCH,
YOU KNOW.
JUST SAYIN'.
I'LL REMEMBER THIS.
- [sinister laugh]
[rooster crows]
SEE YOU LATER, DUDE RANCH.
- IT'S BEEN REAL.
- I HAD A GREAT TIME
WITH YOU ALL.
- SOME KIDS'LL HAVE FUN
WITH THAT.
- FROM BEGINNING TO END,
THE DUDE RANCH WAS SO MUCH FUN.
- I DID ENJOY
THE HORSEBACK RIDING,
EVEN THOUGH I WAS TERRIFIED.
THE FACT THAT I DID IT
AND I OVERCAME IT--
THAT MAKES ME HAPPY.
- ME TOO.
- I FEEL LIKE MORE OF A MAN NOW,
OFF THE DUDE RANCH.
- WE SURVIVED.
- WE SURE DID.
- [yawns]
- ADIOS, AMIGOS.
- HELLO.
I REALLY WANT TO GET
A DNA TEST.
IF I'M AN ALIEN, THAT WOULD BE
THE BEST CASE SCENARIO,
BECAUSE I'VE ALWAYS
WANTED TO BE AN ALIEN.
I'M NOT FROM CHILE.
- NO, YOU MIGHT'VE BEEN
BORN THERE, BUT--
- I'M NOT EVEN CHILEAN.
- I NEED A GAY JOEY NIGHT.
- IT'S LIKE A TWERK PARTY
RIGHT NOW.
- WE'RE CATWALKIN'.
- AHH!
- OH, MY GOD,
YOU LOOK LIKE JWOWW.
- OH, MY GOD.