- BABE, CAN YOU ALLOW ME
TO ADOPT A BABY?
- JUST SO WE'RE CLEAR ON THAT,
WE AND ARE SIMPLY
LOOKING INTO IT AS
A POSSIBLE FUTURE ENDEAVOR.
WE WANT TO HAVE
OUR OWN CHILDREN FIRST, CORRECT?
- WHATEVER COMES FIRST.
- THEY'RE BEING GOOD RIGHT NOW.
THIS--NORMALLY
SHE JUST ATTACKS IT.
LIKE, I DON'T UNDERSTAND THIS.
- NO, NO, NO.
I'VE ALREADY STAKED OUT
THE TERRITORY.
I OWNED IT.
- OH, MY GOD.
- I THINK THIS IS MY DRESS.
- IS THIS HAPPENING RIGHT NOW?
OH, ROGER'S GONNA KILL ME.
- I WANT TO GET MARRIED!
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT I LOVE IT *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
[phone line rings]
- HELLO.
- HEY, POOP.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOIN'?
- I'M JUST REALLY EXCITED,
AND I JUST FEEL LIKE I WANT
TO START PLANNING RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE I FOUND
MY WEDDING DRESS,
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO
OR WHERE TO START.
- AWW...
- JENNI STOPPED
PLANNING HER WEDDING
BECAUSE IT WAS
SO STRESSFUL,
BUT I JUST NEED HER ADVICE,
LIKE WHERE DO I GO?
SHOULD WE START
LOOKING AT VENUES?
LIKE, I NEED YOUR HELP.
- I MEAN, I'M NOT
A PROFESSIONAL OR ANYTHING,
BUT I COULD ALWAYS
SHOW YOU WHAT I DID
AND KIND OF, LIKE,
DO THE STEPS THAT I DID
TALKING TO THE PEOPLE
THAT I TALKED TO.
THAT MIGHT HELP.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT'LL BE, LIKE--
- I'D LOVE THAT.
- OH, YOU WOULD?
- YEAH.
- PLANNING A WEDDING
IS VERY STRESSFUL,
TO THE POINT WHERE I QUIT.
SO--
- THAT SUCKS.
- GOOD LUCK, BOO.
- I DON'T LIKE BEING STRESSED.
- DO YOU WANT TO GO TODAY?
I HAVE NOTHING TO DO TODAY.
- DUDE, THANK GOD.
I REALLY CAN'T
FOLD ANY MORE SHIRTS.
- * I'D BE LOST *
* WITHOUT YOU *
* BY MY SIDE *
- WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
- YOU MEAN WHAT I WANT?
- YEAH.
LIKE WHAT'S YOUR DREAM WEDDING?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- I WAS NEVER LIKE,
"OH, I ALWAYS ENVISIONED
THIS AND THIS."
LIKE, I'M NOT THAT LOSER.
- I HEARD THE THREE MOST
EXPENSIVE THINGS ABOUT A WEDDING
ARE THE FOOD, VENUE,
AND FLOWERS.
- CAN'T I DO
ARTIFICIAL FLOWERS?
- THIS IS KIND OF COOL.
- I'M KIND OF SCARED
OF HEIGHTS RIGHT NOW.
JENNI'S BRINGING ME
TO ONE ATLANTIC,
AND THIS IS THE VENUE
THAT SHE WOULD GET MARRIED AT
IF SHE WANTED TO GET MARRIED.
- BEAUTIFUL, RIGHT?
- THIS IS REALLY NICE.
- HI, WELCOME TO ONE ATLANTIC.
I'M ELIZABETH.
- GREAT TO MEET YOU. JENNI.
- HI, JENNI.
- THIS IS NICOLE.
- HI, NICOLE. WELCOME.
- ELIZABETH IS ONE ATLANTIC'S
WEDDING PLANNER,
WHO IS FABULOUS AND SMALL.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I SAID SMALL.
I'M BEING RACIST.
- WE'D LIKE TO SAY LESS IS MORE
BECAUSE YOU'VE GOT THAT
BEAUTIFUL OCEAN VIEW.
- MORE IS MORE.
- MORE IS MORE, PERFECT.
- HAVE YOU NOT LOOKED AT US?
THERE'S NOTHING ABOUT US
THAT SAYS LESS IS MORE.
- DO YOU ALLOW ZOO CREATURES?
- WHAT KIND OF ZOO CREATURES
ARE YOU THINKING OF?
- ELEPHANTS.
- DO YOU KNOW HOW BIG OF A
[bleep] AN ELEPHANT WOULD TAKE?
- THAT WOULD BE GROSS.
- YES. [laughs]
- A LEOPARD?
- WE CAN FIND OUT ABOUT THAT.
- A LION?
- [laughs]
- MONKEYS?
- MM-HMM.
- THE MONKEYS COULD
PASS OUT THE DRINKS.
- THAT MIGHT BE A PROBLEM.
THE BOARD OF HEALTH
IS NOT GONNA ALLOW THAT.
- OH.
JUST IDEAS, SO--
- I HEAR YOU. YEAH.
- * IF YOU CAN
BREAK THESE BINDS *
* FREEDOM'S
WHAT YOU'LL FIND *
- HEY, MR. SENECA,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- HEY, JIONNI, HOW YOU DOING?
- GOOD, GOOD.
WE WANT TO GET MARRIED.
I DON'T WANT TO COME BACK
TO MY PARENTS' HOUSE,
SO WE'RE BUILDING A HOUSE, AND
WE'RE BUILDING IT FROM SCRATCH.
WE CAN DESIGN IT
HOWEVER WE WANT.
THIS IS GONNA BE GREAT.
DO YOU WANT TO TAKE
NICOLE AND I
MAYBE OVER THERE TO WALK US
THROUGH SOME STUFF?
- YEAH, I THINK
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
WHEN YOU'RE AVAILABLE,
LET ME KNOW.
- OKAY, SOUNDS GOOD.
I'LL TOUCH BASE WITH YOU LATER.
- MOMENTS LIKE THIS MAKES ME
REALLY FEEL LIKE AN ADULT.
WE'RE GOING TO MEET OUR
CONTRACTOR TO BUILD OUR HOUSE.
I MEAN, I'M AN ADULT NOW.
[singing] * YOU'RE GONNA
GET A HOUSE SOON *
* YOU'RE GONNA
NO MORE GRANDMA'S HOUSE.
- LET THE PLANNING BEGIN.
SO HAVE YOU THOUGHT
ABOUT ANYTHING YET?
THE COLORS, THE LOOK, THE FEEL.
- I DON'T KNOW YET.
- YOUR SAVE-THE-DATES,
YOUR MENU CARDS,
THE LINENS, CHARGERS
ON ALL OF THE TABLES.
- WHAT'S A CHARGER?
- LOOK BEHIND YOU.
YOU'VE GOT SOMETHING TO PUT
ALL OF YOUR ENTREE PLATES ON.
- IT'S JUST FOR SHOW?
- YEAH.
- YEAH, IT'S ANOTHER
DECOR ITEM.
- I WOULD USE IT FOR SALAD.
- [chuckles]
- DO YOU HAVE PICTURES
OF, LIKE, PAST WEDDINGS?
- WE DO, ABSOLUTELY.
- OH, I LIKE THAT.
IT LOOKS LIKE INDIA.
- YEAH.
- THESE INDIAN WEDDINGS HAVE
ALL OF THOSE BEAUTIFUL GOLD,
ALL THOSE VIBRANT COLORS.
- DETAILS THAT YOU
WEREN'T THINKING.
- WE SHOULD BE INDIAN.
THIS IS SO FUN.
I WANT A PARADE.
- YOU CAN HAVE A PARADE.
- I'M SURE YOU'RE GONNA
GET A PARADE.
- [laughs]
- DEFINITELY LOTS
OF THINGS TO DECIDE.
- HOW DO YOU FEEL?
- OVERWHELMED.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- JUST GOT TO TAKE IT
ONE STEP AT A TIME.
- THINK I'M GONNA HAVE A STROKE.
MY ARM HURTS.
- [chuckles]
HEY, WELCOME TO MY WORLD.
THIS IS WHY I PUT MINE ON HOLD.
[laughter]
- YOU READY FOR YOUR
TRAINING WITH THE GURU?
WE'RE GOING TO SEE
THE DOG TRAINER
AGAIN FOR THE SECOND TIME,
BUT I HAVEN'T DONE
ANYTHING WITH THE AIR HORN.
I ALREADY FAILED.
NOW I GOT TO CRAM FOR CLASS.
SIT, DOWN, STAND,
LAY D--LONG D--
UGH, THEY'RE NEVER
GONNA KNOW THIS. OKAY.
I WAS A VERY BIG PROCRASTINATOR
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
BACK OFF.
I FIND PROCRASTINATION
IS THE MOST
EFFICIENT WAY
OF DOING SOMETHING.
[blows air horn]
YEAH.
GET YOUR ASS
TO THE GRASS RIGHT NOW.
BECAUSE LIKE BAM,
I'M GONNA GET THIS [bleep] DONE
AND THEN BE DONE.
[blows air horn]
- LET'S GO SEE OUR NEW HOUSE.
THANK YOU.
- I HELPED DESIGN
THE BLUEPRINTS.
I DID A LOT OF
THE BLUEPRINTS AND CHANGING.
- WE.
- WE HELPED DESIGN--WE HELPED
DESIGN THE PLUE-PRINT--
- I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
- WHAT?
- LOOK AT THIS.
THIS IS OUR STREET.
THIS IS THE GARAGE?
- RIGHT HERE.
WE GOT IT ALL LAID OUT FOR YOU.
[imitates car chirp]
- WE'RE IN OUR GARAGE?
- YOU'RE IN THE GARAGE.
WELCOME TO YOUR NEW HOME.
- I'VE KNOWN JOE MY WHOLE LIFE.
I'VE KNOWN--
- [laughs]
- WHAT?
- MY EARS HURT.
- OKAY.
- I'M SORRY.
- WAY TO RUIN
MY WHOLE ENTIRE THING.
- AW, LOOK AT--
OH, YOU'RE ADORABLE.
- MIXTURE OF BOTH OF YOU.
- YEAH.
- BABE.
- GO. JUST COME ON. JUST START.
- BABE, I'M SORRY.
- I'M NOT MAD.
I'M JUST NOT REDOING IT. GO.
- THIS IS THE FRONT DOOR.
- YEAH, THIS IS
YOUR FRONT ENTRANCE.
- DING DONG.
- [laughs] MAIN FOYER.
STAIRS GOING UP ON THIS SIDE.
- CHANDELIER.
- BIG CHANDELIER.
STAIRS GOING DOWN
ON THE OTHER SIDE.
YOU GOT YOUR DINING ROOM
OVER HERE
WHERE YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE A DINNERS.
AND OVER HERE,
YOU GOT YOUR LIVING ROOM,
AND THEN THIS IS
YOUR MONSTER KITCHEN AREA.
- WE'RE BOTH COOKERS.
WE LIKE COOKING.
- WE'RE COOKERS?
- WE BOTH LIKE [laughs]--
- NO, YOU'RE A COOKER.
- SHUT UP.
- I CAN'T COOK.
- CABINETS ALONG THE BACK WALL,
CABINETS ALONG THE SIDE.
- NEXT QUESTION.
- YEAH, J, DON'T PUSH HER OFF.
I KNOW YOU MIGHT WANT TO.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S HIGH ENOUGH.
- AM I UPSTAIRS?
- DO YOU LIKE THE VIEW?
- YEAH, NOW YOU'RE ON
THE SECOND FLOOR.
- LOOK AT YOUR VIEW.
LOOK AT YOUR MOMMY UP THERE.
WHAT IS YOUR MOMMY DOING?
- [screams]
- OH, MY GOD.
ONLY FOUR STEPS.
[laughs]
- I MISSED A FEW.
I THOUGHT I HAD IT,
AND I DIDN'T.
- OH, MY GOD.
- I GOT SCARED.
- * ALL THIS BEING GOOD
WON'T STOP ME *
- UGH, I JUST WANT TO DROP YOU
OFF WITH THE GURU FOR A WEEK.
MAMA NEEDS A BREAK.
NO BARKIN'.
HEY.
- HEY, BEAUTIFUL.
- WHO'S THAT?
- HELLO.
LOOK WHO'S NOT BARKING.
- I KNOW.
WELL, LOOK WHAT I CARRY.
- OH, MY GOD.
OH, LOOK AT THE DIFFERENCE.
OH, YES, YOU CAN KISS ME.
- I FEEL LIKE MY DOGS TALKED
TO EACH OTHER AND SAID,
"WE'RE JUST GONNA
MAKE MOM LOOK LIKE
AN [bleep]
IN FRONT OF THIS GUY."
- OH, AND TONGUE TOO.
WE'LL DO TONGUE.
- JUST BECAUSE WE KNOW
HOW MUCH IT'LL PISS HER OFF
IF WE'RE GOOD
WITH EVERYONE ELSE BUT HER.
- DO ME A FAVOR, PICK HER UP.
I'M REALLY CURIOUS NOW.
- OH, IF SHE'S GONNA
COME AFTER YOU.
- HELLO.
WHO'S GOOD?
OH, HO, HO.
YOU WANT TO DO IT AGAIN?
I DON'T--
- STOP IT RIGHT NOW.
- HEY, HERE IT IS.
- OOH.
- DON'T YOU DO THAT TO HER.
DON'T--PUT HER DOWN.
- BAD!
- BELLA'S A BITCH
JUST LIKE MOMMY.
YOU KNOW, RAISE THEM
LIKE YOUR OWN, AND&amp;
- OOP--
- SHE'S THE SPITTING IMAGE
OF ME RIGHT NOW.
- LET'S TAKE DIESEL.
- DON'T!
- OH, MY GOD, DIESEL!
[blows air horn]
- STOP IT.
- LET HIM GO.
LET HIM GO.
AH!
- DIESEL!
- HOLD ON!
- ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND?
THIS IS WHY NO DOGS LIKE YOU.
DIESEL IS MENTALLY CHALLENGED.
IT'S FINE.
HE'S OUR--HE'S OUR BABY, BUT YOU
KNOW, HE'S--HE HAS PROBLEMS.
SO THE NEXT TIME,
I CIRCLED THE SECTIONS
YOU NEED TO JUST TRY
AND WORK ON AS BEST YOU CAN
TO GET THEM PAST THE TEST.
SOCIALIZATION AND TRAINING.
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
ALL THE EQUIPMENT STUFF
THEY'LL PASS WITH NO PROBLEM.
- AS LONG AS IT MAKES
MY DOGS BETTER.
- IT WILL.
- SO WHEN DO YOU START,
LIKE, BUILDING STUFF?
- YOUR HOUSE?
IN ABOUT FOUR WEEKS, WE'LL START
BREAKING GROUND ON YOUR HOUSE.
- WHAT'S "BREAKING GROUND" MEAN?
- DIGGING.
WE'LL START BUILDING.
- LIKE THE BASEMENT?
- THE FOUNDATION.
- OKAY.
- BUT WHEN DO, LIKE,
STICKS GO UP?
- WALLS?
[laughter]
- WALL STARTS
ABOUT THE SAME TIME.
- SO WE CAN, LIKE,
DRIVE BY AND SEE THINGS.
- I HOPE YOU--I HOPE
YOU DON'T USE STICKS.
- EXACTLY, YEAH.
- NOT STICKS, WOOD.
- DA-DA, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- HE JUST WANTS TO CRY.
HE NEVER ACTS LIKE THIS,
I SWEAR.
- [crying]
[laughter]
- WHAT IS HE DOING?
- GOOD TO SEE YOU GUYS.
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
- YES, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I'M SO EXCITED.
- WE'LL BE TALKING.
- YES, SIR.
- DO YOUR WORK!
- I WILL.
- LET'S GET THIS HOUSE UP.
- IT'S COMING.
- WE GET THE HOUSE,
I HAVE A BABY.
I COULD GET PREGNANT RIGHT NOW.
- AND I BLAME YOU.
I KEEP BLAMING YOU GUYS.
- JIONNI KEEPS TELLING ME
TO PUT IT OFF.
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
- [laughs]
- PLEASE.
LORENZO'S GROUNDED.
- NICOLE.
- I'M KIDDING.
- HE DOESN'T KNOW THAT.
- ARE YOU EXCITED?
- YEAH, BUT WE'RE JUST SIMPLY
GOING TO ASK QUESTIONS, RIGHT?
- UNLESS THEY HAVE 'EM
AVAILABLE.
- THEY DON'T
HAVE BABIES AVAILABLE.
- TODAY, WE'RE OFF
TO AN ADOPTION FAIR.
- IT DOES SOUND WEIRD,
AN ADOPTION FAIR.
- MAYBE YOU THROW A BALL, KNOCK
DOWN SOME CANS, YOU WIN A BABY.
THROW A DART. I DON'T KNOW,
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- BABE.
- MAYBE I SHOULD PUT A SUIT ON.
- IT'S OUTSIDE.
- I KNOW, BUT I--THIS LOOKS LIKE
PEDOPHILE GEAR.
- YOU DON'T
LOOK LIKE A PEDOPHILE.
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT PEDOPHILES LOOK LIKE.
YOU'D HAVE TO HAVE, LIKE,
THE CREEPY VAN.
- WHO'S THIS GUY?
HE PROBABLY HAS A CRIMINAL
BACKGROUND, WHICH I DO, BUT--
- I DO, TOO.
- NO, I ACTUALLY DON'T.
- I DO.
- WE SHOULD PROBABLY
TAKE YOUR CAR
BECAUSE I'LL PROBABLY
SCARE ALL THE KIDS IN MY TRUCK.
- YOU SCARE GROWN MEN
WITH YOUR TRUCK.
- IT'S LIKE A MONSTER
ABDUCTION-MOBILE.
- * ONE MORE TRY SHE SAID *
* OH *
- [singing wedding march]
- [laughs]
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT ARE YOU WEARING?
- THIS IS WHAT
I'M GONNA LOOK LIKE.
- AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED TO
PUT IT OVER YOUR FACE?
- OH.
- SCARY WOMAN.
- YOU EMBARRASSED?
I, NICOLE, TAKE YOU,
JIONNI LAVELLE
[screaming]
TO BE MY HUSBAND.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ARE YOU GONNA DO THAT
DURING THE THING?
- YES.
- YOU JUST KISSED MY CHIN.
THIS IS AWKWARD.
- [laughs]
WE'RE LEAVING LORENZO
WITH MY MOM,
AND ME AN JIONNI ARE GONNA
GO CHECK OUT STONE HOUSE.
IT'S OUR FIRST WEDDING VENUE
THAT WE'RE GONNA
CHECK OUT TOGETHER.
I WANT, LIKE, A HUGE MANSION,
YOU KNOW,
SO IT JUST LOOKS LIKE
I'M A PRINCESS IN A CASTLE.
- THANK YOU FOR COMING.
- NO PROBLEM.
- BUT WE GOT TO PLAN A WEDDING.
- LET'S SKEDADDLE.
- ALL RIGHT. HAVE FUN.
- BABE, I THINK THIS IS IT.
OH, YEAH, LOOK.
- I'M NERVOUS.
- LET'S GO ADOPT A BABY.
- SHUT UP.
- LET'S GO WIN A BABY.
- IT'S NOT--CLEARLY,
YOU DON'T WIN BABIES HERE.
- DO WE JUST, LIKE, ROLL UP
AND JUST TALK TO RANDOM PEOPLE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
THERE'S SOMEONE
THROWING A FOOTBALL.
- OH, I CAN DO THAT.
I'LL BOND WITH THAT GUY.
YOU TALK ABOUT BABIES.
- NO, I'M SCARED.
- THE WALK UP
WAS DEFINITELY AWKWARD.
WE'RE NOT PARENTS.
WE'VE NEVER ADOPTED A CHILD.
IT'S A PICNIC, YOU KNOW,
AND WE DIDN'T BRING
A POTATO SALAD, NOTHING.
- BUT WE SEE A BUNCH OF KIDS
AND A BUNCH OF FOOD,
AND WE'RE JUST CRASHING.
- YEAH, I'M ALL ABOUT IT.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- HI.
- OH, WE'RE DOING GOOD.
HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD.
- NICE DAY.
- I'M ROGER.
THIS IS JENNI.
- HEY, I'M LIZ.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
THANKS FOR COMING, GUYS.
COME ON IN. IT'S ALL--
IT'S A WHOLE BUNCH OF CHATTIN'.
WE'RE GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
- COOL.
- NOW ARE YOU INTERESTED
IN ADOP--IN ADOPTION?
- YEAH.
MY MOTHER WAS ADOPTED,
AND MY BEST FRIEND WAS ADOPTED.
SO I WOULD LOVE TO GIVE A CHILD
THAT SAME LOVE AND CARE THAT,
YOU KNOW, MY BEST FRIEND
AND MOM HAD.
- AT ONE POINT, WE WERE
IN THE SAME STAGE THAT YOU WERE.
WE HAD NO IDEA.
- DO YOU FIND ANY DIFFICULTY
IN, LIKE, THE BONDING
PROCESS OR NO?
- YOU DON'T THINK ABOUT IT.
- YEAH.
- NOTHING FEELS ANY DIFFERENT.
- KNOW AWKWARDNESS, NO--OH, WOW.
- NO.
- BEING HERE, YOU SEE THE
CLOSENESS AMONGST THE FAMILIES.
IT'S A HUGE,
EXTENDED SUPPORT GROUP,
BUT THEY EVEN
CALL EACH OTHER FAMILY.
IT'S A GOOD FEELING.
- OH, ROGER.
- YOU WANT TO TOSS
THE BALL AROUND?
- I'LL RACE YOU, ROGER.
- YOU WANT TO RACE?
I'LL RACE YOU.
WHERE ARE WE RACING TO?
DUDE, I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN RUN THAT FAR.
- [laughs]
- I'M A OLD MAN.
- I HOPE HE DOESN'T
EMBARRASS HIMSELF.
- [laughs]
- GO!
- AH, YOU BEAT ME!
THAT WAS A PHOTO FINISH,
BUT I THINK YOU GOT ME.
- I REALLY THINK ROGER'S
BEEN READY TO HAVE KIDS,
BUT HE'S NERVOUS.
SO I JUST HOPE THAT
DOING THINGS LIKE THIS
WILL MAKE HIM REALIZE
THAT HE SHOULDN'T BE NERVOUS.
- YOU GOT A GOOD ARM.
- SEEING THESE PARENTS AND
THEIR CHILDREN MAKES ME REALIZE
THAT ME AND ROGER COULD BE
THESE PEOPLE ONE DAY.
- YOU WANT TO GO GET HIM TODAY?
- I HATE YOU.
ARE YOU READY TO GET GOIN'?
- SURE, YEAH.
- WELL, THANKS FOR COMING.
- NO, THANK YOU.
- ANYTIME, ANYTIME.
OH, MY GOD.
- GUYS, SO NICE TO MEET YOU.
I'M TAKING YOU UP
ON THAT RACE AGAIN SOON.
OVERWHELMINGLY, I WOULD SAY
WE CAME OUT OF THERE
WITH A VERY POSITIVE EXPERIENCE.
GET A HUG!
LET ME GET A HUG.
[laughter]
- AND, YOU KNOW, IF I WAS
EVER READY TO DO THIS,
NOW I DON'T THINK I WOULD
SECOND GUESS MYSELF.
I THINK I WOULD JUST DO IT.
- SEE YOU GUYS!
- BYE.
- I THINK I MIGHT'VE
STEPPED IN POOP.
- YOU DID?
- I DON'T KNOW. I SMELLED IT.
- SORRY, I HAD TO GO.
- ONE OF OUR MAIN CONCERNS
WAS THE COCKTAIL ROOM.
- I, LIKE,
WANT TO GO TO A WEDDING,
AND THEN I SEE, LIKE,
A LITTLE MENU,
AND YOU HAVE LIKE
THREE ENTREES TO CHOOSE FROM.
- MM-HMM.
- 'CAUSE EVERYONE
HAS DIFFERENT TASTES.
SO I WOULD LIKE THAT.
- OKAY.
- BUT THEN I FEEL LIKE
HE'S GONNA DO ALL THE FOOD.
THAT'S HIS JOB.
- OKAY. SO YOU CAN CHOOSE--
- YEAH, I ONLY GOT ONE JOB
IN THIS WHOLE THING.
- YOU'RE GONNA SELECT
THE ITEMS.
- YOU CAN DO WHATEVER YOU WANT.
- WHAT OTHER DETAILS
HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT?
- UM...
- HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT
THE TYPE OF CEREMONY
AND WHO CAN MARRY YOU?
- NOT REALLY.
- HAVE YOU THOUGHT
ABOUT A PHOTOGRAPHER?
THE TYPE OF CAKE
THAT YOU'D LIKE?
- both: NOPE.
- A BAND OR A DJ?
- THERE ANYTHING THAT'S REALLY
IMPORTANT TO THE TWO OF YOU?
A LOT OF THINGS TO THINK ABOUT.
- I'M SO CONFUSED.
- OH.
- JIONNI'S STARTING
TO REALIZE, YOU KNOW,
WHAT IT TAKES
TO PLAN A WEDDING.
I MEAN, I'VE ALREADY KIND OF
GOT MY ASS HANDED TO ME
WITH THIS,
SO I FEEL LIKE NOW IT'S JIONNI'S
TURN TO BE LIKE, "OH, MY GOD.
WE HAVE A LOT OF [bleep]
TO PLAN."
AND NOW WE CAN WORK TOGETHER
BECAUSE WE'RE BOTH
ON THE SAME PAGE.
- THANKS FOR EVERYTHING, GUYS.
APPRECIATE IT.
- YOU'RE WELCOME.
- WE HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT WE'RE DOING.
[sighs]
- I WOULD REALLY LIKE
A DESTINATION WEDDING.
I WOULD LOVE TO GET MARRIED
IN DISNEY.
DISNEY, FIREWORKS, A PRINCESS.
YOU WANT TO BE A PRINCESS,
WE'RE GONNA BE IN A CASTLE.
WE'LL GET MARRIED IN A CASTLE,
A REAL CASTLE, NOT--
NOT A HIGH CEILING--
- WALT DISNEY CASTLE?
- YES! YES.
- WITH MICKEY
AND MINNIE MOUSE THERE.
- EVEN BETTER.
I'LL MAKE THE PHONE CALL
TOMORROW TO WALT HIMSELF.
- HE'S FROZEN.
- WELL, HE CAN MAKE IT HAPPEN.
- WHY IS HE FROZEN?
- HE'S AN HISTORIC MAN.
HE INVENTED EVERYTHING.
- OH, I THINK THEY FROZE HIM
BECAUSE THEN THEY WANT...
- HE'S THE CREATOR.
HE'S A LEGEND.
- TO MAKE HIM ALIVE AGAIN
IN THE FUTURE FOR MORE CARTOONS.
- IF IT WASN'T FOR WALT,
WE WOULDN'T BE HERE.
NO LION KING,
NO MICKEY AND MINNIE.
- STOP.
- WALT'S EVERYTHING.
- WALT'S A GENIUS.
I WONDER IF THEY'LL
EVER WAKE HIM UP.
- THERE'S MORE
SNOOKI AND JWOWW ON THE WAY...
- AND IT CONTINUES NOW.
- [laughing]
- DA-DA-DA!
OH...
OH, MY GOD...
- MY TURN.
MY TURN. HI.
- [crying]
- STOP IT.
- OH-HO-HO.
- EW, STOP.
YOU'RE SO RUDE.
JIONNI, WALK AWAY.
- EVERY TIME I HAND LORENZO
TO NICOLE, HE JUST CRIES.
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
- BUT YOU LOVE THE FACT
THAT HE WANTS YOU ALL THE TIME.
- NO, I DON'T LOVE IT.
IT JUST--
- YEAH, YOU DO.
YOU DO IT ON PURPOSE.
- [crying]
- BABE, HE WANTS ME.
- NO, HE WANTS ME.
NO.
- MM, MISSED YOU.
IT WAS TOO LONG.
- WHY DOESN'T HE LIKE ME?
- BUM, BUM, BUM, BUM.
- SO WHAT DID YOU THINK
OF THE WHOLE EXPERIENCE?
- I REALLY LOVED IT.
I FELL IN LOVE
WITH ALL THOSE FAMILIES.
- THE KIDS WERE GREAT.
I WAS HAVING FUN
PLAYING WITH THEM.
- THEY'RE AMAZING.
SO NOW WHAT?
- NOW IF YOU ARE OVULATING,
WE COULD GO TRY TO HAVE A BABY.
- I MEAN, WE LITERALLY
JUST LEFT THE ADOPTION PICNIC.
NO, IT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
YOU WANT A BABY NOW?
- NO.
- DIDN'T THINK SO.
- BUT WE CAN PRACTICE
BABY-MAKIN'.
- IT'S SLEEPY TIME NOW.
IT'S SLEEPY TIME.
HERE'S A PAD.
I WANT YOU TO WRITE DOWN THE
THINGS THAT MEAN THE MOST TO YOU
FOR THE WEDDING IN WHAT
YOU REALLY, REALLY WANT,
LIKE WHAT'S IMPORTANT TO YOU.
- IS THIS LIKE
JENNI AND ROGER'S PROBLEM LIST?
- NO.
THIS IS OUR WEDDING.
I NEED TO KNOW WHAT JIONNI
REALLY WANTS TO DO
FOR THE WEDDING,
AND I WANT HIM TO KNOW
WHAT I REALLY WANT TO DO
FOR THE WEDDING.
- HMM.
HOW MANY YOU HAVE?
- ONE.
- ONE?
- [laughs]
- I HAVE SIX
THAT I CAN THINK OF.
- SHOULD I PUT THINGS
THAT I DON'T CARE ABOUT?
- JIONNI.
- [clears throat]
MY WEDDING IDEAS.
GOOD FOOD OPTIONS.
- MM-HMM.
- OKAY.
A BIG COCKTAIL ROOM.
- MM-HMM.
- MY LAST ONE IS--
JUST FORGET IT.
IT'S NOT A GOOD ONE.
- WHAT? TELL ME.
- [chuckles]
A SMALL AFTER PARTY.
- OH, THAT'S WHAT I WANTED.
- IF I'M NOT TOO TIRED.
- ARE YOU [bleep] KIDDING ME?
I MEAN, COME ON.
THAT'S LIKE MY DAD.
- MY DAD, YEAH.
HE'S GETTING OLD, SO--
- IS THAT IT?
- GO AHEAD.
- "WEDDING,"
WITH STARS AROUND IT.
NO MATTER WHERE WE ARE,
I WANT TO PULL UP
IN A HORSE AND CARRIAGE
'CAUSE I'M A PRINCESS
FOR THE DAY.
- YOU DON'T WANT TO JUST
WALK DOWN THE AISLE?
- YEAH.
I'M GONNA PULL UP
IN HORSE AND CARRIAGE,
AND THEN I'M GONNA
WALK DOWN THE AISLE.
- OH, PULL UP. OKAY.
I THINK--
- I'M NOT GONNA GO DOWN THE
AISLE IN A HORSE AND CARRIAGE.
THAT'S TOO EXTREME.
- WELL, BE MORE SPECIFIC.
- OKAY.
HORSE AND CARRIAGE TO RUNWAY.
WHAT'S IT CALLED?
- RUNWAY.
I WANT DRUNK FOOD
FOR OUR GUESTS.
- DRUNK FOOD?
- YEAH, LIKE WHEN--THE MUNCHIES.
- OKAY.
- I WOULD LIKE TO MAKE BABY
NUMBER TWO AFTER OUR WEDDING.
- LIKE THAT NIGHT?
- YEAH. LIKE, I WANT A BABY.
- GOD.
- I WOULD LOVE
TO WRITE OUR OWN VOWS.
- WRITE OWN VOWELS?
- WRITE OUR OWN VOWS.
- WELL, THERE--WE GOT
TO COMPROMISE ON THAT.
- OKAY.
- I'M GONNA WRITE THINGS
I DON'T WANT TO DO.
- WHAT WOULD YOU NOT
WANT TO DO AT A WEDDING?
- SAY MY OWN VOWELS.
- JIONNI.
- ALL RIGHT.
IT WAS A GOOD S--
A GOOD DAY, A GOOD START.
I FEEL LIKE NICOLE AND I
COVERED A LOT.
I'M VERY HAPPY WE'RE
ON THE SAME PAGE TOGETHER.
- [blows raspberry]
[gasps]
CAN YOU CARRY ME UP THE STAIRS
LIKE WE JUST GOT MARRIED?
- LET'S GO, MRS. LAVELLE.
- OH, MY GOD.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
MY LAST NAME'S GONNA CHANGE.
THAT'S SO WEIRD.
[giggles]
[laughs]
JIONNI, PLEASE.
I'M GONNA [bleep].
PLEASE DON'T DO THIS.
PLEASE.
SHH, THE BABY.
[farts]
YOU'RE--[laughs]
YOU FARTED.
[laughing]
STOP.
OH, [bleep].
- TODAY, WE ARE GONNA BE
DOING A PUPPET SHOW.
YEE-HAW!
- YOU'RE A HORSE, NOT A DONKEY.
- [laughs]
- I WOULD HONESTLY LOVE
IF WE COULD KIND OF GIVE ROGER,
LIKE, A BABY BOOT CAMP.
- I'M TOTALLY DOWN FOR THAT.
ROGER, THE BABY POOPED.
ROGER, LORENZO
THREW UP EVERYWHERE.
- HE WANTS TO
PUNCH US ALL IN THE FACE.