- OH, MY GOD!
- AAH! HE TOOK A STEP!
- HE'S GONNA WALK THIS SUMMER.
- I'M GONNA CRY.
- ARE YOU GONNA GET
ALL THE GIRLS?
- NO.
- HE'S SO HANDSOME,
ISN'T HE?
- ARE YOU FLIRTIN'?
[laughter]
- ALL RIGHT, KIDS,
I'M READY.
IT'S DEFINITELY HARD TO LEAVE
LORENZO WITH A STRANGER.
I WONDER HOW HE'S DOING.
- GIVE HER A FEW MINUTES.
HER BOYFRIEND
PROBABLY JUST GOT THERE.
- OH, PLEASE!
- IF THERE'S ANYBODY HERE WITH
US, MAKE YOUR PRESENCE KNOWN.
[loud clang]
- AAH!
WE NEED TO GET THE HELL
OUT OF HERE.
OOH! HONEY, HELP!
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- SOMEONE JUST BLEW
ON MY NECK.
[Icona Pop's I Love It]
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* *
* I DON'T CARE *
- WHICH ONE'S WHICH?
AAH!
* BOM-BOM-BOM-BOM-BOM *
- THIS IS A GOOD POTATO.
[laughs]
THIS IS A GOOD POTATO.
- YOU'RE ACTING LIKE
I DIDN'T DO ANY WORK.
- IT WAS A STEP UP FROM
THE NACHO SALAD.
- YOU DON'T LIKE
MY NACHO SALAD?
- NO, I'M SAYING
IT'S A STEP UP.
LIKE, YOU--YOU--YOU--
- OH, YEAH.
IT'S MORE ADVANCED.
- MORE, YEAH.
[blowing raspberries]
- I HAVE NEWS.
- WHAT?
OH, GOD.
- WE'RE RUNNING TO AC
WHOO!
- WHO?
- ME AND JENNI.
- OH, MY GOD.
IS THAT WHY I GOT ALL THIS
TREATMENT TONIGHT?
- NO, I'M JUST--THIS IS
OUR FIRST KIND OF NIGHT.
- I KNEW THIS--I KNEW THIS
WAS FOR A REASON.
- NO, IT'S NOT, ACTUALLY.
I'M JUST TRYING TO COOK
FOR YOU AND BE A WIFE, BUT--
- YEAH, RIGHT.
YOU JUST WANT THE OKAY.
- I DON'T NEED AN OKAY.
- YES, YOU DO.
- I KNOW IN THE BACK
OF JIONNI'S MIND,
HE'S LIKE, "I HOPE
SHE DOESN'T GET TOO DRUNK
AND, YOU KNOW,
KISSES HER GIRLFRIENDS."
THANKS FOR LETTING ME GO
TO AC.
CHEERS.
- I WILL NEVER SAY NO.
- I KNOW.
TOO STRONG?
I'M TRYING TO GET LUCKY
TONIGHT.
- COVER YOUR EARS.
YOUR SON'S HERE.
- HEY, I'M DYING.
- YOU'RE NOT DYING.
- I CLOGGED THE TOILET.
- YOU WHAT?
YOU WHAT?
- I CLOGGED THE TOILET.
- YOU CLOGGED THE TOILET?
- YEAH.
- WHAT, DID YOU HAVE
A MASSIVE [...]?
- YES.
- THAT--MAYBE THAT'S
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU.
- MAYBE I HAVE
A [...] VIRUS.
I DEFINITELY STILL WANT TO GO
TO ATLANTIC CITY
WITH MY GIRL, EVEN THOUGH
I FEEL LIKE [...].
I NEVER GET SICK LIKE THIS,
AND I MEAN, I'M THINKING,
AM I PREGNANT?
BUT I CAN'T BE,
BECAUSE WE DON'T DO IT, SO--
- WE DON'T "DO IT"?
- WE DON'T DO IT ENOUGH
TO WHERE
I COULD GET PREGNANT.
AND PLUS, I'M ON BIRTH CONTROL.
- IT ONLY TAKES ONE.
- I LOVE YOU GUYS SO MUCH.
I LOVE YOU.
OW!
- [laughs]
BYE.
WAVE.
[horn honks]
- I LOVE YOU!
- LOVE YOU!
[horn honks]
- FINALLY!
OH, ATLANTIC CITY,
HERE WE COME.
- [groans]
I GOTTA GO
TO THE BATHROOM.
SAVE ME!
- EHH! WAAH!
- SAVE ME!
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- CAN I USE YOUR BATHROOM?
'CAUSE I HAVE TO [...].
- [gasps]
- YOU HAVE DIARRHEAS?
- BAD.
RAIN ON MY PARADE,
A POOL PARTY.
- I CAN'T PUT ON
A BIKINI RIGHT NOW.
WHAT IF I [...] MY PANTS
AND IT, LIKE, RUNS DOWN MY LEG
AT THE POOL PARTY?
- [gasps]
- WE'RE GOING TO AC, BABY.
WHOO!
- [crying]
- HI, DADA.
WE GOTTA CALL UNCLE ROGER
TO SEE WHAT HE'S DOING.
EH!
DADA!
- HEY, WHAT'S UP, BUDDY?
- ROGER!
- I'M AT THE BARBER SHOP.
I JUST GOT OUT OF WORK.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK WE, UH,
DO SOMETHING
BEFORE THE GIRLS GET BACK.
- YOU WANT TO GO PLAY
PAINTBALL?
- YEAH, MAN.
- ALL RIGHT, MAN.
LET'S DO IT. I'M IN.
I'M GAME.
- ALL RIGHT. SOUNDS GOOD.
BRING YOUR GAME FACE.
- ALWAYS, MAN.
MY WAR FACE IS ON.
- WE'LL DO IT
TILL WE BREAK.
- I FEEL LIKE YOU HAVE
AN UNFAIR ADVANTAGE TO ME,
'CAUSE YOU'RE, LIKE,
HALF MY SIZE.
- YEAH? WAIT TILL YOU SEE
WHAT I BRING.
THEY CALL ME "JOHN RAMBO,"
SO DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT IT.
- [crying]
- BYE.
- EH!
- SAY BYE.
DADA, I GOTTA RECORD YOU
FUSSING AROUND, OKAY?
I'M RECORDING LORENZO
KIND OF CRYING, MOANING.
JUST IN CASE NICOLE CALLS ME
AND SAYS, "HOW'S THE BABY,"
I'M JUST GONNA PLAY THAT.
MOMMY DOESN'T KNOW
I'M GOING PAINTBALLING.
- [crying]
- IT'S PERFECT.
KEEP GOING, KEEP GOING.
- [crying]
- GOOD.
KEEP DOING THAT.
- [crying]
- YOU KNOW, I COULD BE OUT,
PAINTBALLING,
AND IF I PLAY THE RECORDING,
SHE'LL THINK I'M WITH HIM.
THIS IS A GREAT PLAN.
- [crying]
- OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
THAT'S PERFECT.
- [babbles]
- YAY!
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
ANTI-DIARRHEA?
- YOU'RE GONNA
SAY "ANTI-DIARRHEA"
SO THEY KNOW
WE HAVE DIARRHEA?
- I MEAN,
WE'RE ADULTS HERE.
I FEEL LIKE SINCE
IT'S A HOTEL IN AC,
A LOT OF PEOPLE
WEAR DEPENDS
AND GO THROUGH
THE SAME PROBLEM,
SO DON'T JUDGE.
- SAY "STOMACH PROBLEMS."
- THEN THEY MIGHT GIVE YOU
SOMETHING ELSE.
- ALL RIGHT, SAY, "PISS
DIARRHEA OUT OF MY ASS," THEN.
[phone ringing]
- THANK YOU FOR CALLING
ESSENTIALS. JESSICA SPEAKING.
- HI, JESSICA, I WAS
WONDERING IF YOU GUYS CARRY
ANTI-DIARRHEA MEDICINE.
- YES.
- CAN THEY DELIVER?
- CAN YOU DELIVER?
- OH, WE DON'T DELIVER
RIGHT NOW.
- CLEARLY,
IF YOU HAVE DIARRHEA,
YOU DON'T WANT TO WALK TOO FAR
AWAY FROM THE BATHROOM.
I DON'T WANT TO GO
TO THE STORE.
THAT MEANS I'VE GOT TO GO
ALL THE WAY DOWN,
ALL THE WAY UP.
SOMETHING COULD HAPPEN
IN BETWEEN
THAT WE DON'T WANT.
- I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD PUT
SOME UNDERWEARS ON.
- YOU NEED A DIAPER.
YOU AREN'T EVEN
WEARING A DIAPER?
- NO. DO I HAVE, LIKE,
A BROWN STAIN ON MY ASS?
DO I?
- NO.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- YEAH.
- YOU NEVER KNOW.
- HAVE YOU EVER "SHARTED"?
- YEAH.
- [laughs]
- YOU KNOW HOW MANY TIMES
I'VE BEEN HUNG OVER?
I'M LIKE,
"UH, I GOTTA FART,"
AND THEN IT'S JUST
DRIBBLING DOWN MY LEG.
LIKE, COME ON.
- [laughs]
THANK GOD NICOLE DOES NOT HAVE
A BROWN STAIN ON HER PANTS.
I DON'T EVER SUGGEST WEARING
WHITE WHEN YOU HAVE PROBLEMS
IN THAT AREA.
IT LOOKS VERY TROPICAL.
- YEAH.
I'VE NEVER FELT THIS BAD
IN MY LIFE.
LIKE, MY BODY
JUST IS SO WEAK.
[...], I FEEL LIKE
WE SHOULD MAKE DRINKS,
GET A LITTLE BUZZ ON,
AND MAYBE HAVING
A MARGARITA
WILL MAKE ME FEEL BETTER.
- WELCOME TO
MARGARITAVILLE.
both: HI.
- ALL RIGHT.
YOU NEED A FEW MINUTES
TO DECIDE ON DRINKS,
FIGURE IT OUT?
- WELL, I WOULD LIKE
TWO EMPTY SHOT GLASSES.
- TWO EMPTY SHOT GLASSES?
- YEAH.
- YOU GOT IT.
- WE HAVE STOMACH PROBLEMS
TODAY.
- OKAY.
THAT'S GOOD TO KNOW.
- EVERYONE HAS DIARRHEA
ONCE IN THEIR LIFE.
- YEAH.
- WE'RE ONLY HUMAN.
- HIT ME HIGH.
- ALL THE WAY?
- AS MUCH AS YOU'RE DOING.
- I DON'T KNOW
HOW MUCH WE TAKE.
LIKE A FULL CUP?
- NO!
- OH. LIKE, HALFWAY.
- THAT'S [...] UP.
THAT'S FINE.
- CHEERS.
THREE YEARS AGO, WE WOULD BE
TAKING SHOTS ON THE TABLE,
ANNOYING CUSTOMERS,
AND NOW WE'RE TAKING
SHOTS OF MEDICINE.
I MEAN, WE'RE LIKE
OLD PEOPLE NOW.
I USED TO DRINK
AND BE FINE.
- YOU NEVER DRANK
AND WERE FINE.
YOU SLEPT TILL 5:00
IN THE AFTERNOON EVERY DAY.
- WHOO!
- MOM?
- YEAH?
HI, JI, HOW ARE YA?
- I'M GOING PAINTBALLING
WITH ROGER.
CAN YOU BABYSIT?
ROGER AND I WANT TO
GO PAINTBALLING TOMORROW.
IF I DO GET IN TROUBLE,
AT LEAST I COULD SAY
I CALLED MY MOTHER
TO COME BABYSIT.
- ALL RIGHT, I'LL GET DOWN
THERE, UM--
I'LL GET DOWN THERE
SOMETIME IN THE AFTERNOON.
- WELL, I GUESS WE'RE GOING
PAINTBALLING.
[laughs]
- YAY!
WHO KNEW THAT HAVING
A MARGARITA
WOULD MAKE ME FEEL BETTER?
DO YOU HAVE THE KEY?
- YES.
- SO, TONIGHT WE'RE GOING
TO A GAY CLUB,
AND GAY CLUBS ARE SO MUCH BETTER
THAN REGULAR CLUBS.
- SERIOUSLY. WE JUST WANT TO
HAVE GIRLS NIGHT.
NO GUYS THAT ARE GONNA, LIKE,
YOU KNOW,
TRY AND BE ALL UP ON THIS.
- YEAH.
both: WE'RE TAKEN.
- [laughs]
[applauds]
- MY LIFE IS COMPLETE!
I WANT MY JOEY.
I FEEL LIKE
I'M CHEATING ON HIM.
- IT'S QUIET.
SO, RIGHT WHEN WE
GET TO THE CLUB,
NOBODY'S THERE.
I'M LIKE, COOL.
BUT THEN AGAIN, I JUST WANT TO
HAVE A FUN TIME WITH BOO-BOO,
SO, EVEN THOUGH IT'S DEAD,
IT'S ACTUALLY
LIKE A GOOD THING.
- GIRLS!
- HI.
- HOLA.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- I'M BRITNEY.
- I'M ROBYN.
- THIS IS ROBYN.
WE'RE A MOTHER
AND DAUGHTER TEAM.
- I LIKE YOUR BOOBIES.
- YEAH!
- SO, TWO DRAG QUEENS
COME UP TO US
THAT LOOK LIKE ROGER
AND JIONNI
IN MAKEUP AND WIGS.
I MEAN, LET'S BE REAL.
- CHEERS, JERSEY GIRLS
IN THE HOUSE!
- CHEERS, BITCHES!
- WORK.
- THE QUEENS ARE TRYING TO
GET US INTOXICATED.
- SERIOUSLY.
BLEHH.
- YOU LOOK HOT AS A BLONDE.
- AH!
- ME AND JENNI ARE HAVING
A BLAST RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE DANCING,
WE'RE ORDERING SHOTS.
- GETTING OUR GROOVE ON
WITH THE QUEENS.
I'M HAVING A FABULOUS TIME.
- ME TOO.
AAH!
[laughs]
- PHOTO SHOOT. READY?
GET IT. WORK IT.
- AAH!
- WHEN YOU SEE ME
FALLING ASLEEP AT A CLUB
WITH MUSIC
POUNDING BEHIND ME,
IT'S TIME TO GO.
BRRR.
NICOLE'S FINE.
SHE NEEDS THIS.
SHE'S A MOM.
IT'S MY NEW ACCESSORY.
IT'S WET.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
[club music playing]
* *
THERE'S A LOT OF ALCOHOL
IN MY SYSTEM RIGHT NOW.
I WISH I COULD GET
THIS SANGRIA,
JUNGLE JUICE
OUT OF MY STOMACH.
- RRARR!
- HI!
- ARE YOU SLEEPIES?
- I SAVED YOU A SPOT.
- THANKS, BUD.
- LOOK! LOOK!
- ME AND JENNI
ARE BOMBED RIGHT NOW.
- [laughs]
- THIS IS WHAT I PICTURED
OUR GIRLS' NIGHT TO BE.
GET AWAY!
- DID YOU HAVE FUN?
- I HAD A LOT OF FUN.
- LOOK, MY [...].
- [laughs]
I DON'T CARE.
[snorts]
- LISTEN,
I WANT ASPARAGUS.
- [laughs]
[seagulls crying]
- I HAD SO MUCH FUN
LAST NIGHT.
I DON'T EVEN
REMEMBER MUCH,
BUT I JUST REMEMBER DANCING
AND CATWALKING.
I WOKE UP
WITH DIRTY FEET.
- MY BUTT HURTS.
MY BUTT IS VERY--
WHAT IS IT?
RARE? RAWR? SORE?
[laughs]
[sighs]
LIFE IS SO HARD.
- IT REALLY IS.
- HELLO?
OH, GOD.
YOU'RE REALLY CARRYING THIS
TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
- I'LL DO WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO WIN.
THIS IS LIKE THE HUNGER GAMES
WITH ME AND ROGER.
I'M--I'M SURVIVING.
I NEED TO LOOK INTIMIDATING.
IF ROGER SEES ME, HE'S GONNA BE
SCARED RIGHT NOW.
HE'S GONNA BE PETRIFIED.
- [laughs]
IS THAT A KNIFE?
YOU GOT A NECK KNIFE?
WHAT'S UP, BUDDY?
- JUST IN CASE.
THEY CALL ME
JOHN [...] RAMBO, OKAY?
I HUNT GUYS LIKE YOU.
- [laughs]
[grunts]
GOT YOU IN THERE.
I'M GONNA SHOOT
THE [...] OUT OF YOU.
NUT SHOTS ALL DAY.
- BUST? OH, COME ON.
- I'LL HOLD.
- HI, DO YOU MIND
IF I JOIN YOU?
- SURE.
SORRY IF WE SMELL.
WE'RE HUNG OVER.
AS THE DAY PROGRESSES,
I FEEL LIKE MY HANGOVER
JUST GETS WORSE AND WORSE.
- LIKE, WHY IS THAT?
- I DON'T KNOW WHY.
I DON'T KNOW.
- IT'S SUPPOSED TO GO
THE OPPOSITE WAY.
- I KNOW.
- OH! GOT A BLACKJACK.
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- AW, IS THAT YOUR HUSBAND?
- OH, IS THAT YOUR HUSBAND?
- YES.
- HOW LONG HAVE YOU
BEEN TOGETHER?
- 21 YEARS.
- AW!
- SEE? IT HAPPENS.
DO YOU STILL HAVE SEX?
- IT GETS BETTER--
OF COURSE WE DO.
IT GETS BETTER
AS YOU GET OLDER.
- THEY STILL HAVE SEX.
- REALLY?
- GOOD FOR YOU.
AMAZING.
THEY STILL HAVE SEX.
- BETTER SEX.
- AND I THINK--I THINK
THAT'S FABULOUS.
AND IT'S PROBABLY
WRINKLY.
- DON'T EVEN GO THERE
WITH WRINKLES.
- OH!
- [groans]
- SHE'S SCARED
TO GET MARRIED,
'CAUSE SHE THINKS
SHE'S GONNA GET DIVORCED.
- WELL, WE DRIVE EACH OTHER
[...] NUTS.
- WELL, THAT'S THE WAY
IT SHOULD BE.
- RIGHT? IF IT DIDN'T--
IF IT WASN'T LIKE THAT,
THAT'D BE WEIRD.
- THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
- THAT'S HOW I TAKE IT.
- SEE?
- YOU'D BE BORED.
IF YOU DON'T FIGHT,
THAT MEANS YOU DON'T CARE.
- THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
FIGHTING IS A GOOD THING,
'CAUSE THAT MEANS
YOU'RE IN LOVE
AND YOU'RE VERY PASSIONATE.
- YOU'RE GONNA BE FINE.
- THANK YOU.
- ENJOY IT
AND FIGHT LIKE HELL!
- IF YOU DON'T FIGHT,
YOU DON'T CARE.
- EXACTLY.
- SO, ME AND ROGER
MUST REALLY BE IN LOVE.
- MM-HMM.
GO HARD OR GO HOME.
WE WENT HARD LAST NIGHT,
NOW WE GOTTA GO HOME,
'CAUSE I FEEL LIKE [...].
- HOW ARE YA?
- WHAT'S UP, FELLAS?
- BIG TARGET.
- YEAH. LITTLE TARGET.
- YEAH, YOU CAN USE THAT
TO YOUR ADVANTAGE!
- WHAT'S THE ADVANTAGE?
- I FEEL LIKE IT'S
ALMOST LIKE GOLF.
I SHOULD HAVE A HANDICAP,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
'CAUSE I'M SHOOTING
AT, LIKE,
A COMPRESSED,
LITTLE SIZE OF A MAN.
ALL RIGHT,
YOU READY, BITCH?
YOU'RE GOING DOWN.
- I'M GONNA [...] YOUR ASS UP.
- IT'S LIKE PLAYING PAINTBALL
WITH A GARDEN GNOME.
- 3, 2, 1, GO!
- LET'S GO, LET'S GO, LET'S GO!
COME ON!
[paintball gunfire]
- WHERE ARE YOU, ROGER?
I'M JUMPING, I'M DIVING,
I'M HIDING, I'M FLIPPING.
I AM JOHN RAMBO.
[paintball gunfire]
- COME ON, BITCH!
YOU CAN'T HIDE ALL DAY!
WE'RE IN THE HEAT
OF BATTLE.
EVERYWHERE YOU LOOK,
THERE'S PAINTBALLS,
THERE'S SMOKE GRENADES
GOING OFF.
IT'S JUST CARNAGE
RIGHT NOW, MAYHEM.
- EAT [...]!
- YOU GOTTA ADVANCE,
BITCH!
YOU JUST CAN'T HIDE THERE
ALL DAY!
[paintball gunfire]
- KILL! YEAH!
YEAH!
- [laughs]
- GOING DOWN.
- "GOING DOWN."
SHE SOUNDS SO DEPRESSED.
THANK YOU, SIR.
- YOU'RE SO KIND.
CHIVALRY ISN'T DEAD.
- I JUST HAD AN AMAZING TIME
WITH MY BOO.
- GOOD TIMES.
I HAVEN'T HEARD
FROM ROGER.
I HOPE HE'S HAVING FUN.
[overlapping shouts]
[paintball gunfire]
- [shouting]
- NO? DON'T LIKE IT?
- HEE-EH.
- I'M SO TIRED.
I'M GONNA CALL JIONNI.
[paintball gunfire]
- HEY, ROG, TIME! TIME!
HELLO.
- HI, BABE.
WE'RE 25 MINUTES AWAY.
- OH, ARE YA? ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE DOING GOOD.
- ARE YOU WITH ROGER?
- YEAH, WE'VE BEEN
TOGETHER ALL DAY.
- WHERE ARE YOU?
- WE'RE JUST CHILLING
AT THE HOUSE.
- COULD I SAY HI
TO LORENZO?
- OH, HE'S, UH,
KIND OF FUSSY RIGHT NOW.
- ALL RIGHT.
- WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
YOU GUYS SOUND TOO NICE
RIGHT NOW.
- YEAH, SERIOUSLY.
- BABE--BABE,
HE'S GETTING FUSSY.
HOLD--HOLD ON.
- OH.
- AW.
- LORENZO, I MISS YOU.
- I GAVE HER THE RECORDING
AND SHE FELL FOR IT.
- SHE DID FALL FOR IT.
- IT WORKED.
- IT DID WORK.
- COULDN'T DO IT WITHOUT YOU.
- PAH-POW!
[both laugh]
WELL, WE GOTTA GET
OUT OF HERE, MAN. COME ON.
- LET'S GO.
THE GIRLS ARE ON THEIR WAY.
I THINK WE COULD MAKE IT BACK
BEFORE THEY GET THERE.
- DON'T DOUBT
MY DRIVING SKILLS, SON.
- YEAH, WE COULD DO IT.
I MEAN, WE'RE GONNA
PULL THIS OFF.
- OH, YEAH.
LET'S GO, LET'S GO,
LET'S GO!
WE GOTTA GO, WE GOTTA GO,
WE GOTTA GO, PEOPLE!
- I JUST WANT TO KISS
JIONNI.
- AW.
- YOU HAVE TO GET THERE
BEFORE THEM.
WE ARE "FUNK."
- [laughs]
- WE'RE ALMOST HOME.
- ALREADY?
- YEAH.
- COME ON!
- GO, BABY, GO!
- LOOK AT THIS TRAFFIC, MAN.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
- WE'RE GONNA BE DIVORCED
BEFORE WE GET MARRIED.
- THERE'S MORE
SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW ON THE WAY...
- AND IT CONTINUES NOW.
- SO, HOW MUCH TROUBLE
YOU THINK WE'RE GONNA BE IN
WHEN WE GET BACK HERE?
- IF WE MAKE IT ON TIME,
WE COULD--WE COULD WEASEL
OUR WAY OUT.
- I KNOW.
- BUT IF WE PULL UP
AND THEY'RE SITTING THERE,
I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT DO WE--
WHAT DO I SAY?
- DOES EVERY LIVING CREATURE
HAVE A BUTT HOLE?
- I FEEL LIKE, YEAH.
EXCEPT FOR, LIKE,
ORGANISMS, MAYBE.
[belches]
- I KNOW THIS BACK ROAD
RIGHT HERE.
THIS'LL CUT OFF
A LITTLE TIME.
- ROGER LIVES
AROUND HERE.
LET--LET--LET'S TAKE
SOME SHORTCUTS.
LET'S BEAT THESE GIRLS HOME.
- DO FROGS HAVE BUTT HOLES?
- GOTTA GET RID OF THE WASTE
SOMEHOW, RIGHT?
- I DON'T KNOW, BRO.
- I MEAN, I THOUGHT--
- I THINK I'M GOOD.
I DON'T THINK JENNI'S
GONNA GET TOO MAD.
- LIKE, I THREW OUT
[...] IN THE BAG.
I WAS--I WAS PLAYING
THE BABY CRYING.
I-I-I HAD THIS
ALL PLANNED OUT.
- WE STILL GOT A SHOT
AT BEATING THEM, SO...
- LORENZO'S BUTT HOLE
IS CUTE.
IT'S LIKE A...
- BALLOON?
- YEAH. BUT IT'S,
LIKE, LITTLE.
- AND SHE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW
JANIS IS THERE?
- SHE HAS NO IDEA.
- HONEY, WE'RE HOME.
- BABE?
- SURPRISE.
- [gasps]
SO, RIGHT WHEN I WALK
INTO THE HOUSE,
I SEE JANIS
HOLDING LORENZO,
AND I'M LIKE,
"WHERE'S JIONNI?"
WHERE'D THEY GO?
- [gasps]
TO PLAY.
- TO PLAY WHAT?
OH, YOU BROUGHT FOOD.
- WHAT'D THEY DO?
- WHAT DO YOU CALL THAT?
PIT BULL? PAINT--PAINTBALL.
- I WAS REALLY, REALLY EXCITED
TO SEE JIONNI,
AND THE FACT
THAT HE'S NOT HERE,
AND HIM AND ROGER ARE OUT
DOING BOY THINGS, I MEAN,
I'M ANNOYED.
I JUST WISH HE WOULD HAVE
TOLD ME.
- I DON'T THINK HE REALLY
WANTED TO GO, JIONNI.
- NO?
JIONNI LOVES THAT STUFF.
- YEAH.
- JANIS IS TRYING TO SAVE
HER SON RIGHT NOW.
- I JUST WISH HE TOLD ME.
- WHOSE BABY WAS CRYING
IN THE BACKGROUND?
- IT WAS PROBABLY ROGER,
GOING...
- IT WAS PROBABLY
YOUR HUSBAND, PROBABLY.
- YEAH, BUT ROGER
CAN'T HIT THAT HIGH NOTE,
AND YOU THOUGHT
IT WAS LORENZO.
- MAYBE IT WAS A--
- A TAPE?
- A DEER.
AN ANIMAL.
I DON'T KNOW.
- IF WE MAKE IT,
THIS IS ONE HELL OF A DAY.
- [laughs]
- IF WE DON'T...
- I'M GONNA [...]
AND SIDESTEP THIS THING
INTO YOUR DRIVEWAY.
BUH-BUH-BUH-BUH!
- DO YOU THINK WE SHOULD
HIDE THE CAR?
MOVE IT ON ANOTHER ROAD,
SO THEY DON'T KNOW WE'RE HERE
AND THEN PRANK THEM?
SO, I REALLY WANT TO BUST
THE BOYS WHEN THEY GET HOME
BECAUSE THIS IS ANNOYING.
THEY LIED TO US,
AND YOU DON'T LIE
TO YOUR FIANCE.
THAT'S JUST ANNOYING.
SO, WE'RE GONNA
GET THEM BACK.
ALL RIGHT, I PARKED THE CAR
AROUND THE BLOCK.
- OKAY.
- SO, THEY'RE NOT GONNA
KNOW WE'RE HERE.
IF YOU WANT TO PRANK US,
WE'RE GONNA PRANK YOU BACK,
BITCHES. JERKOFFS.
- WHAT IS SHE GONNA SAY IF SHE
SEES MY MOTHER THERE?
- WHAT IS YOUR MOTHER
GONNA SAY?
WHERE'S YOUR MOTHER GONNA
SAY YOU WENT?
- I-I COULD SEE HER
BACKING ME UP,
BUT I'M GETTING NERVOUS.
- I'M NOT EVEN WORRIED
ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE STRESSING ME OUT
'CAUSE YOU'RE STRESSING OUT.
- SHOULD I CALL THE BOYS?
BE LIKE, "WE'RE ALMOST HOME.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?"
- SURE.
- TWO CAN PLAY THIS GAME.
- OH, [...].
- DID SHE CALL AGAIN?
- YEAH.
HELLO.
- HI, JIONNI.
- HI.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- NOTHING. JUST HANGING.
- WE'RE GONNA BE HOME
IN, LIKE, 15 MINUTES.
- OKAY. YEAH,
WE'RE JUST HANGING.
- CAN I TALK TO LORENZO?
- UM, HE--HE--HE'S--HE'S, UH...
HOLD ON, BABE.
ROGER'S TRYING TO
CHANGE HIM.
- ROGER DOES NOT
CHANGE DIAPERS.
- HE SAID--HE SAID, UH,
IN HIS--IN HIS--
IN HIS THERAPY, THEY SAID HE
SHOULD START CHANGING DIAPERS.
- OKAY.
JENNI'S MAKING A FACE.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
- IT'LL HELP ME BE
A BETTER FATHER ONE DAY.
- ALL RIGHT,
WE'LL BE HOME SOON.
LOVE YOU. BYE.
- BYE.
- THEY'RE IDIOTS.
- ROGER'S CHANGING
THE DIAPER.
- YEAH, AND LORENZO CAN'T COME
TO THE PHONE RIGHT NOW.
- OKAY.
- OBVIOUSLY.
- 'CAUSE HE DOES THAT.
THEY'RE AWFUL LIARS.
- MM-HMM.
- JIONNI'S NOT SLEEPING HERE
TONIGHT.
- I THINK WE'RE GOOD, BRO.
- [applauds]
- JUST JANIS' CAR IS HERE.
- GOOD WORK, GOOD WORK.
PERFECT IDEA, EXECUTED...
- FLAWLESSLY.
- WE GOT IT.
- BY JOHN T. RAMBO
AND THE TERMINATOR.
IT WAS THE PERFECT
BOYS' DAY OUT,
AND, UH,
NOTHIN' BUT WINNERS HERE.
- WE GOT THIS, BUDDY.
- LET'S GO, LET'S GO.
- WE GOT THIS.
- GO, GO, GO, GO, GO.
- [exhales]
- WHOO!
- [claps]
- LIARS!
- OH, [...].
- CAN WE FILL OUT
APPLICATIONS?
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU GUYS ARE HERE.
- I'M GETTING REALLY BAD
DEJA VU RIGHT NOW.
- [laughs]
- CAN I HAVE A SEC?
- AAH! I DON'T WANT TO DO THIS!
OH, MY GOD, OH,
MY GOD, NO!
OH, MY GOD!
- I THINK THIS IS MY DRESS.
- AND [...]
JUST GOT REAL.
OH, ROGER'S GONNA KILL ME.
- I WANT TO GET MARRIED!