- STOP!
- I LOVE YOU.
- STOP. GET OUT.
YOU HAVE FIVE SECONDS
TO GET OUT OF MY ASS.
- THAT'S A PILLOW.
MY HAND'S BETWEEN TWO PILLOWS.
- STOP. I WANT YOU
TO BE AFFECTIONATE,
NOT 'CAUSE YOU WANT TO GET
SOME ASS.
- THAT'S THE LAST THING
ON MY MIND.
KISS YOU.
- [squeals]
YOU STUPID ASS!
THIS IS NOT ROMANCE.
THIS IS MOLESTATION.
- HOW DOES IT FEEL,
WAKING UP TO THIS?
- STOP!
[Icona Pop's I Love It]
- * I DON'T CARE
* I LOVE IT
* I DON'T CARE
* I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE
* I LOVE IT
*
* I DON'T CARE
[dog yapping]
- ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
I CAN'T--YOU GUYS ALL
JUMP EACH OTHER.
SO I THINK I HAVE
THE BEST PLAN EVER.
TO GET MY DOGS
TO GO EVERYWHERE,
I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD GET THEM
CERTIFIED AS SERVICE DOGS.
HEY, YOU GET ON
YOUR SEAT BELT.
BUT FIRST,
I'VE GOTTA TRAIN THEM.
MOVE IT! STOP IT!
SIT! RELAX!
HOW DID YOU GET CAUGHT
UNDERNEATH THERE, HUH?
THERE'S NO HOPE.
- COME ON BACK.
I'LL INTRODUCE YOU.
YOU'LL LOVE THIS.
- OH...
- SIT DOWN!
- YEP.
- SO THIS IS PETE.
PETE, THIS IS JENNI.
- HI.
- WHAT A PLEASURE.
HOW NICE TO MEET YOU.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD.
THEY'RE BEING GOOD RIGHT NOW.
NORMALLY SHE JUST ATTACKS--
I DON'T UNDERSTAND THIS.
- NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
I'VE ALREADY STAKED OUT
THE TERRITORY.
THIS IS MY TERRITORY.
MY DOG IS IN HIS TERRITORY.
AND HE'S NOT GONNA MOVE.
- HE WON'T?
- OH, NO. NO, NO, NO.
HE'S THERE.
- THIS DOBERMAN PINSCHER HAD
BIGGER BALLS THAN MY HEAD.
AND IT, LIKE, COULD EAT
BOTH MY DOGS FOR A SNACK.
AND YET, MY DOGS WOULD NOT
ACKNOWLEDGE HIM.
I HAVE NEVER SEEN THIS
IN MY LIFE.
BEFORE WE WALKED IN HERE--
[dogs yapping]
WHAT DO YOU DO TO THIS?
- AAH, AAH, AAH, AAH, AAH!
GIVE ME THE LEASH.
LOOK WHAT STOPPED IMMEDIATELY
WHEN I TOOK THE LEASH AWAY
FROM YOU.
I DON'T GET THIS.
[dogs stop barking]
YOU DON'T EVEN DO ANYTHING.
AND I'M, LIKE, MEETING
GANDHI OF DOGS,
WHO JUST, LIKE, HAS THIS
PRESENCE, AND EVERYONE SHUTS UP.
- YOU SEE WHAT I JUST DID?
I OWNED IT.
- YOU KNOW, GANDHI.
HE'S IN THE BIBLE.
HE'S THE GUY THAT LIVES
UP IN THE MOUNTAINS
AND GIVES ADVICE FOR FREE.
YOU KNOW, PENIS COVER
WRAPPED AROUND HIM.
ON HIS ROCK...
SOMEWHERE.
OH, MY GOD, ROGER SAID THAT,
"YOU JUST YELL.
YOU DON'T FOLLOW THROUGH."
- YOU SAY IT ONCE--
- DON'T YOU DARE SAY HE'S RIGHT!
- YOU SAY IT ONCE,
MAKE IT HAPPEN.
- I [bleep] HATE
WHEN ROGER'S RIGHT.
SWEAR.
I [bleep] HATE IT.
HOW DO YOU STOP 'EM
FROM BARKING?
- I'VE GOT A SPECIAL TOOL.
IT'S CALLED AN AIR HORN.
THEY'RE ALL BARKING
AT EACH OTHER--EHH! ENOUGH!
THE QUEEN HAS SPOKEN!
- I LIKE BEING THE QUEEN.
- YEAH. SEE?
READY?
- ONE, TWO, THREE, AND GO.
AND SASHAY, AND SASHAY.
I FEEL LIKE A PROFESSIONAL
DOG WALKER.
- GO BACK AGAIN.
SEE, YOU'RE INTERESTING NOW.
WHO'S GOOD?
- THIS IS NOT COOL.
EVERYTHING I'VE DONE
FOR THE PAST FIVE YEARS
HAS JUST TURNED TO [bleep]
IN THREE SECONDS.
YOU CAN'T TEACH AN OLD DOG
NEW TRICKS.
CLEARLY, THAT STATEMENT
IS WRONG.
[dog barks]
UGH.
I GOTTA GO GET AN AIR HORN.
*
- OW!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I'M GONNA TEST OUT
MY BOUNCE SHOES.
- WE'RE PACKING.
OH, MY GOD.
- CAN YOU SEE ME RUNNING
DOWN THE STREET EXERCISING?
- AND I'D LAUGH AT YOU.
THIS ISN'T CALIFORNIA.
PEOPLE WILL THROW [bleep] AT YOU
WEARING THINGS LIKE THAT.
- UGH! OOH!
DON'T I LOOK LIKE A MOM?
- YEP, JUST LIKE ONE.
- I'M DYING.
I'M GONNA BRING THESE.
- * YOU'VE BEEN DIPPING
IN MY LOVE TOO LONG *
*
- EWW! THAT'S A TRAILER?
LOOKS LIKE A HORSE
SHOULD BE IN IT.
THIS IS SO HICK.
- A HORSE CAN'T FIT IN THERE.
AND THERE WAS NO THING
FOR HIS HEAD TO BREATHE.
- OKAY, A PONY. A PONY.
- THERE WAS NOTHING FOR HIM
TO BREATHE IN.
- A DONKEY.
- I'M NOT TALKING
ABOUT THE SIZE.
I'M SAYING HE CAN'T BREATHE.
- [chuckles]
A SHEEP.
- YOU'RE NOT GETTING
THE PURPOSE.
- EWW!
IT SMELLS LIKE DONKEY POOP.
AREN'T I STRONG?
LIKE, YEAH!
[grunts]
WHOA!
ALL RIGHT, YOU GET THIS ONE.
- * PLAYING WITH MY PILLOW
* LOOKIN' FOR NEW WAYS
TO LAY *
* SLEEP
- DID YOU HEAR A BARK?
- NO.
DID YOU TRAIN 'EM TODAY?
- ELECTRIC SHOCK THERAPY.
- NO, YOU DIDN'T.
NO, YOU WOULD NEVER DO THAT.
- I WISH YOU WERE THERE.
I WALK IN THE BACK DOOR,
I MEET GANDHI.
GANDHI OF THE DOGS.
A DOBERMAN IS BEHIND HIM,
JUST SITTING.
NOT ONE OF OUR DOGS BARKED,
LOOKED AT HIM,
OR WENT AFTER HIM.
- SHE LOOKS LIKE
SHE'S ON QUAALUDES.
WHY IS SHE OUT LIKE THAT?
I FEEL FAIRLY CONFIDENT
THAT BELLA IS DEAD RIGHT NOW.
LOOK AT HER. SHE'S DEAD.
OH, NO, THE EYE MOVED.
- YOU SURE THEY DIDN'T
GET DRUGGED?
'CAUSE I'VE NEVER SEEN--
- SWEAR TO GOD.
- OH, MY GOD, THAT IS, HONESTLY,
THE BEST I'VE EVER SEEN 'EM.
- I WOULD NEVER DRUG
MY DOGS.
- I DIDN'T SAY YOU.
I WOULDN'T ALLOW THE GANDHI
TO DRUG MY DOGS EITHER.
- WHEN DID YOU GET JEWISH?
WHERE DID THAT JEWISH SLANG
COME FROM?
- GANDHI'S NOT JEWISH.
- OFF TO THERAPY WE GO.
- * YOU KNOW I JUST WOULDN'T
MISS IT FOR THE WORLD *
- ME AND ROGER ARE HEADING
TO COUPLES' THERAPY,
AND IT'S OUR FIRST SESSION.
- I'M BEING VERY OPTIMISTIC
ABOUT THIS THERAPY SESSION.
- HI, I'M RICK PORESKY.
HOW ARE YOU?
- HEY.
- JENNI.
- WELCOME.
VERY NICE TO SEE YOU.
PLEASE TAKE SEATS.
- YOU KNOW, THE ULTIMATE GOAL
WOULD BE
WE'RE HERE TO GET HELP.
- AND NOT KILL EACH OTHER.
YES.
- SO THESE SESSIONS USUALLY
BEGIN WITH WHAT ARE THE ISSUES?
WHAT ARE THE MAIN THINGS THAT
YOU WANT US TO BE FOCUSING ON?
- YOU WANT TO START THERE,
MY LOVE?
- WE BUTT HEADS 'CAUSE WE'RE
BOTH ALPHA IN OUR RELATIONSHIP.
AND THEN ON TOP OF IT,
IT'S EXPLOSIVE.
- SHE WENT BAT [bleep] CRAZY
AND KICKED THE LIVING HELL
OUT OF THE CLOSET DOOR.
- I WENT JACKIE CHAN ON IT.
- HOW MANY HOLES IN WALLS
OR DOORS ARE THERE
IN YOUR HOUSE?
- I KICKED IN TWO DOORS.
- I THINK I'VE DONE
AT LEAST TWO MYSELF.
THEY ALL GET FIXED IN ABOUT
A DAY 'CAUSE WE'RE SO ANAL.
WE HAVE AN ON-CALL
CONSTRUCTION COMPANY
ON STANDBY, AND KEEPS 'EM
IN STOCK, BASICALLY.
- PRE-PAINTED AND EVERYTHING.
- YEAH.
- YOU FEEL YOU NEED DRAMA,
SO YOU'RE GONNA--
- DRAMA JUST TO GET
ATTENTION,
BECAUSE I FEEL
UNAPPRECIATED.
LIKE KISSING AND HOLDING
AND CUDDLING--IT'S VERY RARE.
THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
- I KNOW THAT I NEED
TO WORK ON ROMANCE.
I KNOW THAT, BUT I JUST WOULD
LIKE TO WALK IN THE ROOM
AND PULL JENNI'S SKIRT DOWN
AND RAVAGE HER.
- UGH.
- AND SHE IS NOTHING ABOUT THAT
AT ALL.
- NO, IT'S TURNING ME OFF
AT THIS POINT.
- I'M EXTREMELY ATTRACTED
TO HER.
- SHE'S A SEXY LADY.
- YEAH, HE WANTS A STRIPPER...
THAT DOESN'T TALK.
- I HAD ALL THE STRIPPERS.
I DON'T WANT THAT ANYMORE.
- I DON'T WANT TO HEAR THAT!
- I DON'T WANT THAT ANYMORE.
I--I WANT A GIRL
THAT LOOKS LIKE A STRIPPER...
- YEAH.
- BUT I CAN SHOW
TO MOM AND DAD TOO.
[laughs]
- YOU HAD STRIPPERS?
- GET OUTTA HERE.
- AS A HOMEWORK ASSIGNMENT,
I WANT YOU GUYS TO MAKE A LIST
OF WHAT YOU WOULD LIKE
TO ACCOMPLISH BEFORE MARRIAGE.
- MAYBE START WITH...
- SEX?
- HOW TO...
- SORRY.
- CONTROL THE ANGER.
- YES.
- SEX WILL BE ON THE AGENDA
FOR NEXT TIME--
- US, OR?
OH, US. OKAY.
- IF YOU'RE INTERESTED.
- [chuckles]
TOUCHE, MY FRIEND!
MAYBE THIS IS WHAT WE NEED
TO SPARK OUR SEX LIFE.
HAVE A THREE-WAY
WITH OUR THERAPIST.
I'M IN IF YOU'RE IN.
[bleep] IT.
- CAN SOMEONE JUST HAVE SEX
WITH HIM
SO HE LEAVES ME ALONE?
I JUST THREW UP IN MY MOUTH.
- [chuckles]
*
- I GOT YOU A LITTLE LIFE VEST,
A BEACH BALL.
AND I GOT A FIRST-AID KIT
FOR YOU.
- OKAY.
- YOU'LL CALL ME BY NEXT WEEK.
- I'LL PROBABLY TEXT YOU
EVERY DAY.
CAN YOU REMIND ME THAT I NEED TO
GO TO CVS BEFORE WE LEAVE?
'CAUSE I NEED TO GET
MY BIRTH CONTROL.
- YES, I WILL DEFINITELY
REMIND YOU OF THAT.
- 'CAUSE IF I DON'T GET
THE BIRTH CONTROL, THEN...
BABY NUMBER TWO.
- NO, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO.
LET'S GO TO THE STORE.
- YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO ASK
MY MOTHER.
IT'S AWKWARD.
- NO, I'M, LIKE,
HER DAUGHTER, KIND OF.
- IT'S AWKWARD.
- WHEE!
- OH, DA DA.
MWAH.
- I'M EXHAUSTED.
- YEAH, I'M TIRED.
SO IS THIS GUY.
- WE SHOULD REST,
GET GOOD SLEEP,
AND THEN WAKE UP
IN THE MORNING
ALL READY TO GO AND EXCITED.
AND THEN WE GET THERE.
- BEDTIME FOR EVERYONE.
- DO YOU WANNA WRITE DOWN
OUR PROBLEMS?
- WE COULD START IT.
HOW 'BOUT THAT?
- THE HOMEWORK?
- THIS IS NOT GONNA BE
ENOUGH PAPER.
- I KNOW. COME ON, LET'S GO
IN THE DINING ROOM.
I'M GOING TO TRY AND TAKE THIS
HOMEWORK ASSIGNMENT SERIOUS.
ONE ASSIGNMENT IS,
I HAVE TO WRITE A LIST
OF WHAT I WANT TO WORK ON
WITH MYSELF.
AND THE OTHER LIST IS
WHAT ME AND ROGER
WANNA WORK ON TOGETHER
AS A COUPLE,
TO, YOU KNOW, BETTER OURSELVES
AND OUR RELATIONSHIP.
GLAD YOU'RE TAKING THIS SERIOUS.
- YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO READ MY LIST.
- THE FIRST THING I NOTICE IS
"JENNI" AND "BUTT HOLE."
SO I CAN IMAGINE
WHAT HIS FIRST THING IS.
WHAT PROBLEMS
DO YOU SEE US HAVING?
- I SEE US STILL IMPROVED
BUT STILL FAILING IN THE
COMMUNICATION DEPARTMENT.
YOU?
WHAT DO YOU GOT?
- PATIENCE.
YOU NEED TO WORK
ON YOUR PATIENCE,
AND SO DO I.
- OH, OKAY,
I WAS GONNA SAY.
A LACK OF INTIMACY,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I FEEL LIKE--I FEEL LIKE
MAYBE YOU HAVE A REASON
FOR NOT RECIPROCATING, EVEN
THOUGH I WOULDN'T [bleep] YOU
AT ANY GIVEN MOMENT.
- [groans]
WHO SAYS THAT
TO THEIR FIANCEE?
COME ON! THAT MAKES ME NOT
WANT TO GIVE YOU ANYTHING.
SMELL MY FINGERS.
- OH!
THAT'S THE CLOSEST
I'VE GOTTEN TO SEX.
[inhaling deeply]
- [laughs]
- WHY DO YOU
COMPLICATE STUFF?
WE'RE MEN, BABE.
WE'RE SIMPLEMINDED PEOPLE.
- NO.
- WE ARE.
- ALL RIGHT, BABY,
LET'S GO TO BED.
- WHO AM I DATING?
I'M GONNA BECOME
A LESBIAN AFTER THIS.
DID YOU JUST FART?
OH, MY GOD,
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
- [laughs]
- * OH, WHAT A DAY, OH,
WHAT A DAY, OH, WHAT A DAY *
- SIT.
SIT.
- YOU PUSHED HER ASS
TO THE GROUND.
- BABE, IT'S A PROCESS.
- [laughs]
- IT'S A PROC--IT'S LIKE
TRYING TO TEACH ANNE FRANK.
IT WAS A [bleep] PROCESS.
SHE WAS BLIND AND DEAF.
PICTURE THEM
BLIND AND DEAF.
SIT.
ANNE FRANK.
SIT. NO.
SSS--
[groans]
HELEN KELLER!
THAT'S WHO I MEANT.
[bleep] ME.
I KNEW I HAD IT WRONG.
OH, THE JEWISH GIRL
IN THE ANNEX.
SIT.
- WOULDN'T A CATTLE PROD
WORK QUICKER?
- SHE'LL GET IT ONE DAY.
- SHE'LL BE RIDING
A UNICYCLE IN DAYS.
- I HOPE YOU GET SHOT
IN THE FACE ONE DAY.
- [laughs]
- * COME BACK HOME TO ME
* AND I WISH
THAT YOU WOULD *
* COME BACK HOME TO ME
- [grunts]
- THIS IS IT, BABY.
LET'S DO THIS.
- BYE. I LOVE YOU.
- BE CAREFUL.
IF YOU NEED ANYTHING, CALL ME.
- OKAY.
SEE YOU SOON.
- BE CAREFUL, DRIVING.
MAKE SURE YOU CALL ME
AS SOON AS YOU GET THERE.
- THIS IS THE MOMENT WE'VE
BEEN WAITING FOR FOREVER--
MOVING OUT OF THE BASEMENT.
- AND DON'T WORRY ABOUT
UNPACKING EVERYTHING
ALL AT ONE TIME.
JUST RELAX A LITTLE BIT.
- LIKE, [bleep] FINALLY.
[horn honks]
- HE BETTER DRIVE SLOW.
[rock music]
- THERE IT IS!
*
- I CAN'T WAIT TO OPEN
THIS HOUSE AND GET IN AND--
- OPEN THE HOUSE?
IS IT A PRESENT?
- SHUT UP!
- WELCOME HOME, LORENZO.
WHEE!
- WOW!
- THIS IS GONNA BE
OUR HOUSE FOR THE SUMMER,
AND THIS IS GONNA BE
OUR TEST RUN
TO SEE IF WE CAN ACTUALLY
DO THIS.
WANT TO SEE OUTSIDE?
WOW!
OH, MY GOODNESS!
LOOK AT THE WATER.
HE'S SO HAPPY!
- WE'RE ON THE WATER.
IT'S NICE, IT'S CLEAN.
- IT'S CLASSY.
WELCOME HOME!
- I MEAN, YOU CAN'T ASK FOR
A BETTER SUMMER HOUSE.
- IT'S PERFECT.
- HEY, YOU.
- HELLO?
- HI.
- WE JUST GOT HERE,
AND I WANT TO
SEE YOU GUYS
AND ALSO, WE NEED
HELP WITH OUR STUFF, SO...
- OH, IT'S ONE OF THOSE?
"I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU, BUT
YOU GOTTA PUT IN THE EFFORT."
- EXACTLY.
LIKE, I LOVE YOU SO MUCH,
BUT [bleep] HELP ME, BITCH.
- THEN I'LL BE RIGHT OVER.
- 'KAY. LOVE YOU. BYE.
- LOVE YOU. BYE.
- I'M GONNA TAKE
A [bleep] REAL QUICK.
IT'S, LIKE, COMING OUT.
[groans]
- BABE?
- YES?
- NICOLE JUST CALLED ME.
- OH, YEAH?
- THEY'RE AT THEIR BEACH HOUSE,
IF YOU WANT TO GO OVER
AND HELP 'EM UNPACK
AND STUFF.
- DID THEY HELP US
MOVE IN HERE?
- DON'T BE THAT FRIEND.
I THINK IT'S 50:50
WITH NICOLE.
SHE DEFINITELY WANTS TO SEE US,
BUT DEFINITELY WANTS OUR HELP.
- MORE 80:20.
DEFINITELY WANTS OUR HELP.
20% OF HER WANTS TO SEE US.
- WELCOME TO MI CASA!
- YO!
- I LOVE IT!
HI.
- HI.
- GOD, YOU'RE, LIKE, HALF
THE HUMAN BEING YOU USED TO BE.
HOW ARE YOU?
- IS THAT A NEW HAIRSTYLE?
- YEAH, I SWITCHED IT OUT.
GOING CORPORATE.
- DIFFERENT.
YOU SHOULD SEE JIONNI'S HAIR.
- HI.
- WHAT'S UP, BUDDY?
- THIS IS STILL HIS PLAYROOM.
- HI, BUDDY.
- WHAT'S UP?
- HI, BABE.
THIS HOUSE IS BEAUTIFUL.
- CRAZY AFRO.
- YOU LIKE IT?
- [laughs]
I WENT THE OPPOSITE.
I CUT MINE OFF.
- THIS IS OUR KITCHEN.
- [making kissing sounds]
I'M REALLY EXCITED
TO SEE LORENZO,
BECAUSE, OH,
I JUST LOVE HIM.
- [coos]
- OH, YEAH?
- GIVE HIM, LIKE,
THE HEAVY ONE.
- IS THIS THE--OH,
WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU GOTTA TELL ME WHERE IT GOES.
ALL UPSTAIRS OR--?
- THIS IS HEAVY.
- OH, I DON'T KNOW.
[rock music]
- HI.
I MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
*
PEEK-A-BOO!
[kissing]
- [groans]
*
- [clears throat]
- HI.
WHAT, CARRY BOXES AND UNPACK
OR WATCH MY GODSON?
- I LOST MY BOOBS.
- GET SOME BOLT-ONS
LIKE JENNI.
- I HAVE TO WAIT TILL
I HAVE ALL MY KIDS.
- ARE YOU GONNA HAVE MORE SOON,
OR YOU DON'T KNOW?
- YEAH.
- SOON? YEAH?
- WELL, WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT THE WEDDING,
AND THEN, MY WEDDING NIGHT,
I WANT TO GET IMPREGNATED.
- WHEN ARE YOU GUYS
GONNA GET MARRIED?
- [laughs]
WE--
- YEAH, I HEARD YOU GUYS DON'T
EVEN WANT TO GET MARRIED NOW.
- YOU WANT TO STAY ENGAGED,
THOUGH, RIGHT? OBVIOUSLY.
- ABSOLUTELY. I HAVE NO QUALMS
OR ISSUES WITH THAT WHATSOEVER.
- DID YOU SAY "QUALM"?
WHAT THE [bleep]
IS A "QUALM"?
- YOU SOUND LIKE VIETNAM.
- "QUALMS."
- WHAT THE [bleep]
IS A "KWON"?
- [laughs]
- THEY FLIRT A LOT.
- THEY'RE FLIRTING
RIGHT NOW?
- NO, 'CAUSE IF THIS
WAS FLIRTING,
THE END RESULT
WOULD BE SEX.
- SHE SAID YOU GUYS
HAVE SEX ONCE A WEEK.
- WHAT?
- [laughs]
I KNEW IT!
- HONESTLY,
LOOK ME IN THE FACE,
AND YOU TELL ME WE HAVE
SEX ONCE A WEEK.
- YEAH, NO, BUT,
LIKE, ONCE A WEEK,
ONCE EVERY OTHER WEEK,
YEAH.
- OKAY, ONCE A WEEK
AND ONCE EVERY OTHER WEEK ARE--
- IT DEPENDS ON THE WEEK.
IT DEPENDS IF
I HAVE MY PERIOD TOO.
YOU CAN'T HAVE SEX
THAT WEEK.
- YOU ONLY GET THAT
ONCE A MONTH,
AND IT'S ONLY FOR, LIKE,
THREE DAYS.
- IT'S, LIKE, A WEEK.
- YEAH.
- IS IT, REALLY?
FOR SEVEN DAYS? OH, MY GOD.
- SEE?
THIS IS WHAT I DEAL WITH.
- THERE'S MORE SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW
ON THE WAY...
- AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
[Lorenzo crying]
- I'M GONNA GO PUT HIM DOWN
FOR A NAP,
'CAUSE HE'S TIRED.
- BYE, LORENZO.
- CAN YOU PUT HIM DOWN FOR
A NAP, WHILE YOU'RE AT IT?
- SERIOUSLY.
[Lorenzo shrieks]
[Snooki screams]
- WELL, NOW I KNOW WHERE
HE GETS IT FROM.
- WHOO!
LORENZO NEEDS TO LAY DOWN
FOR HIS NAP
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
HE HAD A BIG DAY.
WE'RE MOVING IN.
AND ME AND JENNI,
WE JUST NEED TO CATCH UP
ON SOME GIRL TIME
ON THE PATIO.
TELL ME MORE ABOUT THIS
COUPLES THERAPY.
- HE NEEDS TO BE
MORE AFFECTIONATE
OR IT'S NOT GONNA WORK.
- MM-HMM.
IT'S JUST ALL GUYS.
- NO, 'CAUSE I'VE MET GUYS
THAT ARE JUST GENUINELY--
YOU KNOW, YOU NEVER LOOK
AT SOMEONE
WHO'S LIKE, OH, THAT'S SUCH
A GREAT COUPLE, LIKE--?
- NOT REALLY?
- NO.
- 'CAUSE I FEEL LIKE ME
AND JIONNI'S RELATIONSHIP
IS PERFECT.
I MEAN, I WOULD LIKE HIM
TO BE MORE AFFECTIONATE.
- ODDLY ENOUGH,
ME AND NICOLE
KIND OF HAVE THE SAME
RELATIONSHIP PROBLEM.
WE BOTH WANT
MORE AFFECTION.
THE ONLY DIFFERENCE IS,
NICOLE IS THE SUBMISSIVE ONE
IN HER RELATIONSHIP,
AND I WILL NOT SUBMIT
TO ANYONE.
I-I WROTE DOWN WHAT I NEED TO
WORK ON IN MY RELATIONSHIP.
- MM-HMM.
- WHAT ROGER NEEDS TO WORK ON.
AND WHAT, AS A COUPLE,
WE NEED TO WORK ON.
I PUT,
MY COMMUNICATION WITH HIM,
MY TEMPER, MY SELFISHNESS,
MY INDEPENDENCE,
MY LAZINESS, AND I NEED TO BE
MORE SPONTANEOUS.
- DID HE HAVE TO MAKE
THE SAME LIST?
- YEAH.
- SO, WHAT'S ON HIS LIST?
OR, YOU DIDN'T SEE IT?
- I DON'T KNOW IF I'M SUPPOSED
TO SHARE THESE OR NOT,
BUT--AND YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
TAKE THIS SERIOUS.
- [laughs]
- THIS IS ISSUES I WISH
JENNI WOULD WORK ON.
NUMBER ONE, I HAVE, "JENNI WILL
NOT LET ME IN HER B[bleep]."
- [laughs]
IT'S ACTUALLY TRUE.
- OH.
- I'M ACTUALLY A LITTLE
UPSET OVER THAT.
- HE WROTE ON MY LIST.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- HE WROTE ON
MY LIST, "BE MORE FLEXIBLE,
"LEARN HOW TO PUT MY FEET
BEHIND MY EARS,
BE MORE OPEN TO ORAL SEX."
- EVERYTHING IS SEX
WITH THIS GUY.
- "BE MORE OPEN TO HEINIE SEX."
- THAT'S SO ANNOYING.
EW! HOW DO YOU DEAL WITH THAT?
- SEE? THIS IS WHY I--
- EWEY. I WOULD WALK AWAY.
- [laughs]
- AT LEAST THREE TIMES A DAY,
EVERY DAY,
I'VE GOT TO HAVE SEX
WITH HER.
- GET OUT OF HERE.
- NEVER, EVER WORKS OUT.
FIRST THING IN THE MORNING,
WHEN I WAKE UP,
I TRY TO HAVE SEX
WITH JENNI.
I COME HOME FROM WORK.
USUALLY, YOU KNOW,
I'LL COME IN THE BATHROOM.
- SHE'LL BE, LIKE,
DOING HER MAKEUP.
I'LL DROP HER DRAWERS.
NOTHING.
"GET THE [bleep] OFF ME."
SWINGING AT ME
WITH THE HAIRDRYER AND [bleep].
- I'M WAITING FOR A HUG
AND A KISS, AND "I LOVE YOU."
- AND FLOWERS.
- AND FAT-FREE CANDY.
- AND WHEN I DO GET IT,
THERE'S ZERO PARTICIPATION.
- OH, MAN,
YOU CRACK ME UP.
- AND THEN,
WHEN I DO DO IT,
IT SOUNDS LIKE
[bleep] DINOSAURS.
- YEAH, IT SOUNDS TERRIBLE.
- IT'S ABUSIVE.
- I WONDER WHAT
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT?
- WHAT WE JUST SAID,
BUT FLIP IT.
- TRUE.
- MM-HMM.
- ROGER,
YOU WANT A HOT DOG?
- IF YOU'VE GOT A BURGER,
I'LL TAKE A BURGER.
- YEAH, LET ME JUST
GRILL THAT.
- I NEED TO GO IN.
- * JUST REMEMBER
* YOU'RE JUST
GETTING STARTED *
* YOU KEEP FORGETTING
- ALL SET.
- YOUR BACKYARD IS AWESOME.
- AMAZING.
- AND PLUS,
LORENZO'S SLEEPING.
LIKE, WE JUST WANT TO RELAX,
HAVE SOME DRINKS.
- BE ADULTS.
- [laughs]
- WHAT?
- THEY'RE HOLDING HANDS.
- I'M TRYING TO EAT CHICKEN,
HE'S HOLDING MY HAND.
- [groans]
- THAT'S SO SWEET.
- I'M TRYING TO MAKE AN EFFORT
TO BE MORE AFFECTIONATE.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE DOGS.
THEY DO SOMETHING YOU WANT,
YOU REWARD 'EM WITH A TREAT.
I LOVE YOU.
- THANK YOU.
- MY TREAT COULD BE SEX.
HARDCORE,
PUNISHING SEX.
- HE DESERVES SOMETHING
TONIGHT.
- OH, GOD,
IT'S ALL ABOUT SEX.
- NO, I DIDN'T SAY [bleep].
- THAT WAS ME.
I SAID HE DESERVES IT.
- OH, GOD.
SO ROMANTIC, SO SWEET.
- WE'RE GONNA HEAD BACK
TO OUR HOUSE, REALLY,
BUT THE SUN'S SETTING
RIGHT NOW,
AND WHY DON'T WE JUST SET OUT
HERE AND WATCH THE SUNSET?
- I'M DOWN FOR THAT.
- DOWN?
- A LITTLE ROMANTIC TIME?
- YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
I'M TRYING TO SET THE MOOD
FOR LATER, WHEN WE GO HOME.
- I HAVE MY PERIOD.
- OH!
- ME TOO.
- IT'S ON THE TAIL END.
- BUT HE DESERVES SOMETHING.
- GOD.
- SOMETHING.
- JIONNI, STAY OUT OF IT.
- * YOUR YOUTH STILL FLOWERS,
YOU'RE AMAZING *
* YOU'RE FASCINATING
WITH YOUR SINCERITY *
- THIS IS SO ROMANTIC.
- EW, BIRD [bleep].
- I LOVE THIS.
THIS IS WHY I'M HERE.
I WANT TO SPEND TIME
WITH MY BOO-BOO MORE.
- IT'S, LIKE,
THE NEW BOOK.
IT'S NOT EVEN A NEW CHAPTER,
IT'S A NEW BOOK.
- YEAH.
WE'RE GROWN UP NOW.
- IT'S LIKE, WHERE'D IT GO?
- IT'S WEIRD.
- NOVELS.
- IS THAT WHAT--
I DON'T [bleep] KNOW.
- IT'S NICE TO BE BACK
AT THE SHORE.
- I NEVER LEFT.
I LIVE HERE.
- TRUE.
BUT WE'RE HERE NOW.
- IT'S NICE
TO HAVE YOU GUYS.
- NOW I GET
MY BEST FRIEND BACK.
- IT'S PERFECT.
TODAY IS THE PERFECT END
TO A PERFECT DAY,
AND I FEEL LIKE THIS PART
IS GONNA BE AMAZING,
WITH MY FAMILY,
WITH MY FRIENDS.
I'M EXCITED.
- WE'RE GONNA HAVE A BLAST.
- I KNOW.
- ALL RIGHT,
LET'S ALL DIVE IN!
- AAH!
- DON'T! NO!
STOP, STOP, STOP!
HEY, STOP!
- WHAT'S THE WORST THAT WOULD
HAPPEN? YOU'D GET WET?
- NO, I'D LOSE AN EYELASH.
- I HAVE TO GET
A BABYSITTER,
AND I'M GONNA
INTERVIEW PEOPLE.
- I'M KENNY.
- HE USED TO WORK AT KARMA.
- OH, REALLY?
- YOU AND I ALMOST
ACTUALLY HAD A MOMENT.
- YOU ACTUALLY DID.
- SWEAR TO GOD.
- MY PAST IS COMING
TO HAUNT ME.
IT'S A [bleep]
HAUNTED HOUSE.
- BAHH!
- AAH! [bleep]!
I NEED JESUS, I NEED PRAYERS,
AND I NEED GANDHI.
AAH!
[loud clang]