- DO YOU WANNA WRITE DOWN
OUR PROBLEMS?
- WE CAN START IT.
HOW ABOUT THAT?
I'M BEING VERY OPTIMISTIC
ABOUT THIS THERAPY.
YOU KNOW, THE ULTIMATE GOAL
WOULD BE TO GET HELP.
- AND NOT KILL EACH OTHER.
- WELL, WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT THE WEDDING.
AND MY WEDDING NIGHT,
I WANNA GET IMPREGNATED.
- WHEN ARE YOU GUYS
GONNA GET MARRIED?
- [laughing]
- YEAH, I HEARD YOU GUYS DON'T
EVEN WANNA GET MARRIED NOW.
- SEE?
THIS IS WHAT I DEAL WITH.
[Icona Pop's I Love It]
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT *
*I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT
*
* I DON'T CARE *
[kids talking]
- SO WE'RE BACK IN SEASIDE.
- LOOK HOW DIFFERENT
IT LOOKS.
I'M EXCITED TO EXPERIENCE
THE SHORE.
IT'S DEFINITELY
GONNA BE DIFFERENT
FROM LIKE OTHER PAST SUMMERS.
JUST, LIKE,
DOING FUN ACTIVITIES
AND REMEMBERING,
BUT NOT GETTING ARREST
- TRUE.
- THIS IS NEW.
THIS USED TO BE THE PIZZA PLACE.
I GUESS...
THEY GOT HURT.
I FEEL LIKE WE HAVEN'T REALLY
SEEN THE BOARDWALK
SINCE HURRICANE SANDY HIT.
- OH, MY GOD!
- THIS IS SO WEIRD.
SO WALKING OUT TO THE BOARDWALK
WITH JENNI,
IT JUST FEELS WEIRD.
LIKE, I ACTUALLY FEEL LIKE
I'M WALKING INTO THE SHORE STORE
TO GO TO WORK.
HEY!
- CAN WE FILL OUT APPLICATIONS?
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU GUYS ARE HERE.
- I'M GETTING REALLY BAD
DEJA VU RIGHT NOW.
- [laughing]
YEAH.
- I DON'T WANNA WORK!
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- I KNOW.
- HOW'S IT BEEN?
- GOOD.
- WELL, GUESS WHAT.
I ALSO HAD A BABY TOO.
- NO, YOU DIDN'T.
- YOU HAD A BABY?
- YES.
- A LITTLE BOY NAMED BRODY.
- AW, THAT'S SO CUTE!
- WE SHOULD DO A BABY DAY.
- I'M DYING TO SEE LORENZO.
I HEAR HE'S GOT
A WHOLE BUNCH OF HAIR.
- HE'S GETTING HAIR
ON HIS BACK NOW.
- OH.
HE'S REALLY ITALIAN.
- [laughing]
WE'RE BOTH PARENTS.
- YOUR MOM AND DAD EXCITED?
- YEAH, SO.
- WHO KNEW?
- THE BABY WAS BORN,
THE BABY WAS NINE POUN--
UH, SEVEN POUNDS.
- DID SHE POOP?
- YES, OF COURSE.
- SHE POOPED?
- SHE POOPED!
- I DIDN'T POOP.
THE FACT THAT ME AND DANNY
ARE PARENTS,
IT'S [bleep] WEIRD.
- GOOD SEEING YOUS.
- YES.
- YOU TOO.
- LOVE YOU.
- BYE.
- SEE YOU SOON.
- LATER.
- IT'S CRAZY HOW TIMES CHANGE.
- * HOO DOO DOO,
HOO DOO DOO *
* DA DA DA DAH
- OH, LOOK,
THERE'S A FEW RIDES.
LET'S GO ON A SCARY RIDE.
RED, WHITE, AND BLUE!
- WAIT, WHAT DOES THAT DO?
- OH, MY GOD.
IT MAKES ME NERVOUS.
IS IT TIGHT?
AM I IN?
- IT'S GOOD, YEAH.
YEAH, YEAH.
- WHERE ARE THE HANDLES?
- BOTH OF YOU ARE GOOD.
- I HAVE A SON!
SO RIGHT WHEN I GET
IN THE RIDE,
I'M LIKE,
YES! I'M SO EXCITED!
OH, GOD.
I CAN'T NOW.
AND THEN WHEN IT STARTS MOVING,
I'M LIKE [bleep] THIS [bleep].
- OH, MY GOD. OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD.
- JENNI, I CHANGED MY MIND!
I THOUGHT I LIKED RIDES.
I FORGOT.
EVERY TIME
WE WENT ON RIDES HERE,
WE WERE ALL DRUNK.
- YEAH. EXACTLY.
- SO I WAS LIKE, WHOA!
BUT SOBER, IT'S LIKE,
OH, MY GOD,
I'M GONNA [bleep] DIE.
[screams]
- [screams]
I DON'T WANNA DO THIS!
- I HAVE A CHILD!
I'M LIKE...
- NO!
- I'M SCARED.
- DON'T DO THIS TO ME!
[both screaming]
OH, MY GOD,
MY [bleep] ARE COMING OUT.
- MOMMY!
- [Lorenzo babbling]
- DA DA?
HA!
LORENZO'S DEVELOPING
PRETTY FAST.
I MEAN,
I KNOW HE'S ABOUT TO WALK.
HE'S CRAWLING.
AND I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE IT.
HE--WHAT ARE YOU--
OKAY.
WHAT TIME'S IT?
DA DA?
WHAT WERE YOU JUST DOING?
ONE...
DA DA.
COME HERE!
DA--AWW.
YOU WERE RIGHT THERE!
- WELCOME TO SEASIDE.
- CHEERS. TO BEING BACK...
- TO A GREAT SUMMER?
- IN SEASIDE.
BEST FRIENDS.
- AND LOTS OF SHOTS.
- I WAS GONNA SAY I MIGHT
BE PREGNANT, BUT I'M NOT.
I'LL BE PREGNANT NEXT...
CHRISTMAS.
- WE MIGHT BE PREGNANT.
YOU NEVER KNOW.
- I THINK IT WOULD BE COOL
IF WE WERE BOTH PREGNANT
BY NEXT CHRISTMAS
TOGETHER.
- THAT'S FINE.
- NO, YOU'RE SCARED
YOUR BODY'S GONNA CHANGE.
- I WANNA ADOPT.
- WHY DON'T YOU WANNA
HAVE YOUR OWN?
- I DON'T WANNA GET FAT.
- THAT'S SO SELFISH.
YOU'RE NOT READY.
- EXACTLY.
- TONIGHT'S THE PERFECT NIGHT
TO BE HERE THOUGH.
- AWW.
- NICE AND BREEZY.
WHAT?
- HAVE YOU BEEN CHEWING ON 'EM
AND PUTTING IT BACK?
- [laughing]
- I BIT AND I'M LIKE,
THIS ALREADY FEELS CHEWED.
- EWW.
STOP.
- IT'S FINE, IT'S FINE.
WE'VE DONE A LOT WORSE.
- * I BELIEVE THAT SOMETHING'S
WRONG WITH YOUR ATTITUDE *
- HEY!
- * YOUR ATTITUDE
- I'D BE LATE
FOR MY OWN FUNERAL.
SO TODAY ME AND ROGER ARE GONNA
DO INDIVIDUAL THERAPY SESSIONS.
I DID MY HOMEWORK.
- GREAT.
- WELL, "I'M PERFECT"...
WAS THE FIRST THING
THAT I WROTE.
AND I HAVE ROGER'S.
OH, WAIT.
- YOU KNOW, I'M MORE OF A GUY
THAT BELIEVES IN JUST...
SAYING IT LIKE IT IS.
I'M NOT INTO LIKE
THAT GAME PLAYING THING.
- I CAN ALWAYS TELL
WHEN HE'S ANGRY,
BUT HE DOESN'T COMMUNICATE
HE'S ANGRY.
I'M ALWAYS LIKE
"WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
"I CAN SEE IN YOUR FACE
THERE'S A PROBLEM.
BUT YOU'RE NOT TELLING ME."
- ISSUES I WISH
JENNI WOULD WORK ON--
NO PARTICULAR ORDER.
JENNI WILL NOT LET ME
IN HER [bleep]HOLE.
- SEX.
- ROMANCE.
HE'S NOT VERY AFFECTIONATE.
WHICH, TO HIM, MEANS SEX.
- YES.
- THIS INCLUDES THINGS
LIKE THE DIRTY [bleep],
THE ALABAMA CRAB DANGLE.
- I WANT
LIKE HUGS AND KISSES.
- STRAWBERRY SHORTCAKE,
[bleep].
- AND I WANT HIM
TO LISTEN TO ME.
- FISH-HOOKING AND [bleep]...
ONLY IN STATES WHERE THEY
ARE NOT CLASS "A" FELONIES.
- YOU'VE LOST ME.
- * I WANT IT PERFECT
- THIS IS HOW MOMMY GOT DADDY
TO NOTICE HER AT THE CLUB.
BOOM, BOOM, BOOM, BOOM,
BOOM, BOOM, BOOM.
AND THEN SHE WENT,
BOOM, BOOM, BOOM, BOOM,
BOOM, BOOM, BOOM,
BOOM, BOOM, BOOM.
AND THEN DADDY WAS LIKE,
"HEY, GIRL."
- [laughs]
ISN'T THAT FUNNY?
- I CAME OVER TO YOU?
- YEAH.
- WHY DON'T YOU RETELL THE STORY
THE RIGHT WAY?
- YOU TELL HIM THE STORY.
HE WANTS TO KNOW.
- YOUR MOM CAME UP TO ME
WITH HER EYES CROSSED,
NOT KNOWING
WHAT WAS GOING ON.
THAT'S HOW IT HAPPENED.
- ABSOLUTELY NOT.
- IF YOU'RE GONNA
TELL THE STORY,
TELL OUR LITTLE BOY
THE RIGHT--
- OKAY, WHAT HAPPENED NEXT?
- WE MADE OUT.
- IT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
- THEN YOU KISSED ANOTHER BOY
AFTER YOU WERE DONE KISSING ME.
- STOP IT.
LORENZO, THAT DID NOT HAPPEN.
- YOU WERE SINGLE.
- I KISSED ANOTHER GIRL TOO.
- JIONNI!
- I'M JUST KIDDING.
[farts]
- DID YOU FART?
- [laughing]
- EWW!
- [farts]
- OH, MY GOD!
ARE YOU KIDDING?
- MY STOMACH HURTS.
- OH, GET OUTTA HERE!
- [laughs]
- YEAH!
LORENZO.
- I'M GONNA GO CHANGE.
- YEAH, YOU BETTER CHANGE
YOUR UNDERWEAR TOO.
YOU STINKY BASTARD!
- OH, MY GOD!
MY FARTS ARE SO LETHAL.
- BABE.
WILL YOU ALLOW ME
TO ADOPT A BABY?
- WAIT A MINUTE.
- ME AND ROGER ALWAYS WANTED
TO HAVE BIOLOGICAL KIDS.
BUT I ALWAYS THOUGHT
OF ADOPTING
BECAUSE NICOLE WAS ADOPTED
FROM CHILE
AND MY MOM WAS ADOPTED.
I JUST DON'T KNOW
THE PROCESS.
- JUST SO WE'RE CLEAR ON THAT,
WE ARE SIMPLY LOOKING INTO IT
AS A POSSIBLE FUTURE ENDEAVOR
THAT WE MIGHT WANNA...
TACKLE.
WE'RE NOT LOOKING
TO ACTUALLY ADOPT ANYTIME SOON,
OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
WE WANNA HAVE
OUR OWN CHILDREN FIRST, CORRECT?
- WHATEVER COMES FIRST.
I MEAN...
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
"WHATEVER COMES FIRST"?
- WE CAN START TRYING
TO HAVE OUR OWN CHILDREN, BUT--
- TONIGHT?
- I'M GONNA PUNCH YOU
RIGHT IN THE [bleep].
- THERE ARE SUCH THING
AS ADOPTION FAIRS.
- THERE ARE?
- MM-HMM.
- WHAT DO THEY ENTAIL?
- HA.
FIRST THING THAT COMES UP
IS "ADOPTION FAIRS
ARE SPEED DATING FOR KIDS."
- I DON'T WANNA SPEED DATE
FOR A CHILD.
- WELL, THERE'S AN AGENCY
ON HERE
THAT WILL ALLOW US
TO SIGN UP
AND DO LIKE AN ADOPTION PICNIC
WITH FAMILIES
WHO HAVE ADOPTED CHILDREN.
- I WOULD LIKE TO DO THAT.
- YOU WANNA CONTACT THIS AGENCY?
- YEAH.
OWWW!
- OH!
I SAW THAT HAPPEN
IN SLOW MOTION.
[laughing]
- OWWW!
- OH!
THAT LOOKED LIKE IT HURT.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I WANNA--I WANNA PUNCH A WALL
RIGHT NOW.
[laughter]
- IN THE HAIRLINE?
- I HIT THE CORNER!
- IN THE HAIRLINE,
OR IN THE--
- IT'S RIGHT ON MY FOREHEAD.
IT'S ABOVE MY EYE.
- OH, THAT'S GONNA
LEAVE A MARK.
LET ME GET YOU SOME ICE.
- OHH!
IS THERE ARE A MARK?
- YES.
- IS THERE REALLY?
- IT HURTS!
- IT'S A TINY LITTLE MARK,
BUT THERE'S A LITTLE PIECE
OF SKIN MISSING.
LITTLE TINY PIECE.
IT'S RIGHT THERE.
- WHO PUTS A CORNER THERE?
- DON'T KNOW.
SORRY.
YOU DID THAT TO YOURSELF.
[laughing]
- I ALWAYS HIT MY HEAD.
THIS IS WHY I'M BRAIN DAMAGED.
- I DON'T KNOW ANYBODY
THAT HITS THEIR HEAD
MORE THAN YOU DO.
- IT HURTS.
- [burps]
"HOW TO PLAN A WEDDING".
OH, MY GOD.
THIS LOOKS LIKE A LOT OF WORK.
MEET CATERERS,
PURCHASE A DRESS.
REGISTER.
SO TODAY'S THE DAY
THAT I'M GONNA START PLANNING
MY WEDDING.
AND I'M REALLY REALLY
EXCITED,
BUT I'M HOPING I DON'T BE
A STRESSED-OUT BRIDE
BECAUSE I WANT EVERYTHING
TO JUST BE HAPPY AND FUN.
BUT I MEAN, ALL THE BRIDES
THAT I TALKED TO,
THEY'RE [bleep] MISERABLE.
RESERVE GUEST ACCOMMODATIONS.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS.
REGISTRY...
[burps]
HOTEL.
UGH!
THIS IS SO ANNOYING.
THIS IS TOO MUCH [bleep].
I NEED HELP.
CASTLE COUTURE.
PRETTY!
THESE ARE LIKE CLASSY.
THE WHOLE WEDDING PROCESS
AND BEING STRESSED
IS JUST LIKE PLANNING
THE FLOWERS AND THE GUEST LISTS
AND SEATING PEOPLE.
THAT'S, LIKE,
THE ANNOYING PART.
THE DRESS PART
IS THE FUN PART.
THIS IS MY WEDDING JESUS.
WHOO!
- * I HAVE SAID MANY THINGS
* TO NUMEROUS GIRLS
* YOU THINK THAT
IT'S BECAUSE I'M WEAK *
- HELLO?
- JOEY!
- HEY, GIRL.
- ME AND JENNI WERE GOING
WEDDING DRESS SHOPPING
AND WE THOUGHT IT WOULD BE
A FABULOUS IDEA
IF WE INVITED OUR JOEYS.
- OH, FUN!
- WILL YOU JUDGE US
AND TRY ON DRESSES WITH US?
- YEAH, OF COURSE!
- I LOVE YOU.
- YOU KNOW
I'M ALWAYS DOWN FOR DRESSES.
- WE KNOW YOU IS.
- ALL RIGHT, LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU.
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU, BYE!
- BYE!
- THERE IS NOTHING
LIKE A GAY MAN'S OPINION.
- OH, I TOTALLY AGREE.
- CAN YOU IMAGINE
IF THEY RIP ONE?
I AIN'T BUYING IT.
- I AIN'T BUYING IT.
FANCY, FANCY.
- I HAVE THE BIGGEST WEDGIE.
HI!
- HI!
WELCOME TO CASTLE COUTURE.
I'M COLLEEN.
HOW YOU DOING TODAY?
- HI!
- SO PRETTY.
- WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
- NICOLE.
- NICOLE, HI. NICE TO MEET YOU.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
- HI. JENNI.
- JENNI, NICE TO MEET YOU.
PLEASURE.
WHY ARE YOU HERE, LADIES?
- PLANNING MY WEDDING!
- YAY! WHEN YOUR WEDDING?
- I DON'T KNOW...YET.
- YOU DON'T KNOW YET.
- I'M ABOUT TO PLAN MINE...
- PROBABLY NEXT YEAR.
- JUST 'CAUSE THIS PLACE
IS SO PRETTY.
- PROBABLY NEXT YEAR,
LIKE AROUND THE FALL TIME.
I FEEL LIKE I'M A VIRGIN
TO EVERYTHING.
LIKE, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO LOOK FOR.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHERE TO START.
AND HOPEFULLY THE PEOPLE
AT THIS PLACE
ARE GOING TO HELP ME.
- [indistinct]
- [gasps]
JENNI!
- OH, MY GOD!
- BRIDESMAIDS' DRESSES.
- WHO IS THAT FOR?
- THAT'S FOR ANYBODY.
- I WANT MY THEME
TO BE BLACK AND GOLD.
- OH, THIS IS PERFECT.
- BEAUTIFUL.
- BUT I DON'T KNOW YET.
IT COULD BE LEOPARD.
- [bleep].
- LIKE A SEXY, LIKE...
- THERE'S NOTHING SEXY
ABOUT STANDING UP THERE
IN A LEOPARD DRESS.
I MEAN, THERE'S SEXY.
- WHO ARE YOU?
- SO BASICALLY, IN THIS ROOM
IS ALL OUR DESIGNER DRESSES.
- WOW!
- LIKE LAZARO, STEPHEN YEARICK,
MATTHEW CHRISTOPHER.
- EVERYTHING IS SO WHITE.
I DON'T WANNA GET MY BRONZER
ON ANYTHING.
- OH, MY GOD.
WHAT--WHAT IF THE--
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
- DO WE GET FINED?
- THANK GOD WE DON'T HAVE
OUR PERIODS.
- WE THROW YOU OUT
OF THE STORE
IF YOU GET BRONZER
ON ANY OF THESE DRESSES.
- SERIOUSLY.
- NO, SERIOUSLY.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW MUCH BRONZER WE USE.
- EVERYTHING IS WHITE,
AND ME AND JENNI HAVE
LIKE SPRAY TANS ON,
WITH BRONZERS ON.
LIKE, WE'RE GONNA [bleep]
THIS PLACE UP.
OKAY, I WANNA TRY 'EM.
- OKAY.
WE CAN TRY ON DRESSES HERE.
- OH, MY GOD.
- OOH! I LIKE THIS.
- [gasps]
I'VE DIED AND GONE
TO BRIDE HEAVEN.
- THIS IS LIKE DRESS-UP.
- TIGHTEN ME UP.
- OKAY, HERE WE GO.
- THIS IS LIKE...
I FEEL LIKE IT FITS GOOD.
I FEEL LIKE
THIS IS EVERY GIRL'S DREAM,
AND I ALWAYS FELT
LIKE I WASN'T THAT GIRL
THAT WAS GONNA LIKE FREAK OUT
OVER WEDDING DRESSES.
BUT I'M FREAKING OUT
RIGHT NOW.
- I KINDA LIKE THIS ONE.
- THIS IS GORGEOUS.
- ISN'T IT?
- IT'S NOT SOMETHING
I PICTURED, BUT...
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
- JUST WANNA MAKE SURE
I DON'T CATCH YOUR SKIN.
- YEAH, BE CAREFUL.
- LET'S TUCK IN THE STRAPS.
- WOW!
- WOW, WOW, WOW.
- NICOLE?
- JENNI?
- READY.
- HOW DO I WALK IN IT?
- HOLD THE FRONT UP...
SO THAT YOU DON'T TRIP.
- MY FAVORITE DRESS
I'M FINALLY TRYING ON,
AND I HAVE GOOSEBUMPS.
MY FIRST DRESS
IS THE DRESS THAT I ALWAYS
THOUGHT I WOULD BUY
IF I WAS TO EVER GET MARRIED.
AND I'M PUTTING IT ON.
AND [bleep] JUST GOT REAL.
- YEP.
- IS THIS HAPPENING
RIGHT NOW?
- IT IS.
- UGH! ROGER'S GONNA KILL ME.
GREAT. COOL.
I'M PLANNING A WEDDING NOW.
- I THINK
IF HE SAW YOU IN THIS,
HE'D KINDA LIKE IT
JUST A LITTLE.
- EWW!
I NEED A XANAX.
- WHERE'S JENNI?
- I'M IN MY DRESS.
- [humming Wedding March]
- [laughing]
- WOW!
I WANT A VEIL!
HOLD ON.
GIMME A VEIL!
I'M ALREADY A BRIDEZILLA.
I'M SO SORRY.
- [laughing]
- GET ME A VEIL!
- * ALL NIGHT
INTO THE MORNING *
- GORGEOUS.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
- I NEED MY JOEY.
- OOH, GIRL!
- JOEY!
[laughter]
- JOEY, I'M IN THE DRESS!
- OH...MY GOD.
- DON'T WE LOOK PRETTY?
- OH, MY GOD.
YOU GUYS LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
- FINALLY, THE JOEYS COME IN.
SO I FEEL LIKE, NOW,
IT'S ON.
IT'S GONNA BE A PARTY.
- HOW MANY DRESSES
HAVE YOU TRIED ON?
- THIS IS THE FIRST ONE.
- IS THAT SILK CHARMEUSE?
- I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT THAT IS.
- THOSE ARE BRIDAL NAMES.
THAT'S REAL BRIDAL FABRIC.
- HE'S RIGHT.
- OH, YOU'RE SO GAY.
- SEE?
- HE'S GOOD.
YOU'RE GOOD, JOE.
- I LIKE THAT ONE.
- I WANNA TRY ON MORE THOUGH.
- OH, I KNOW.
- CAN THEY TRY ON
SOME DRESSES?
- SURE.
- [gasps]
- YES.
- OH, MY GOD.
WHERE'S THE PLUS-SIZE SECTION?
- [laughing]
I FEEL LIKE YOU NEED TO WEAR
AN OFF-WHITE.
- OFF-WHITE?
BECAUSE I SLEEP
WITH SO MANY MEN?
- YOU'RE A WHORE.
- I DON'T THINK
THIS IS MY DRESS.
- JENNI'S BRONZER'S PROBABLY
GETTING ALL OVER EVERYTHING.
- MY NIPPLE'S OUT.
- [laughing]
- SHOULD'VE SHAVED MY CHEST
BEFORE THIS.
- [sighs]
- COMFORTABLE?
- HOLD IT IN, BABY.
HOLD IT IN.
- SUCK IT IN.
- WHAT IF WE WANNA DO
A QUICKIE?
- YOU DON'T CONSUMMATE
BEFORE THE MARRIAGE.
- THIS LOOKS LIKE
A FAT GIRL DRESS.
- WHAT THE [bleep]
IS GOING ON?
- I LOOK LIKE THE FAT GIRL
AT THE PROM.
[laughter]
LOOK AT YOUR BUTT.
- OH, THAT'S HOT.
- OOH, BITCH, YOU'RE A LITTLE
THICK FOR THIS ONE.
- I WANNA GET MARRIED!
- I THINK I CAN SQUEEZE
INTO THE OTHER ONE.
- WHAT SIZE ARE YOU?
- I DON'T KNOW, FAT.
- OOH, WAIT!
- WHY DO YOU ALWAYS END UP
IN YOUR UNDERWEAR?
- THIS IS CRAZY.
- TRYING ON EVERY DRESS,
THEIR BALLS HANGING OUT
EVERYWHERE.
- EW.
- THESE DRESSES
ARE GONNA SMELL LIKE BALLS.
- WELL, THAT'S WHY
THEY'RE SAMPLES.
- [laughs]
I THINK I FOUND MY DRESS.
- OH, MY GOD.
I NEED TO SEE YOU.
[gasps]
OH, MY GOD!
- I THINK THIS IS MY DRESS.
- OOH!
- [humming Wedding March]
- YOU LOOK LIKE A PRINCESS.
- I LOVE IT.
- YOU LOOK SKINNY TOO.
WHICH IS GOOD.
- WHOO-HOO!
- YOU LOOK THE MOST BEAUTIFUL
I'VE EVER SEEN YOU IN.
LIKE EVER.
- I KNOW.
I'M LIKE, HOLY [bleep].
I AM A GORGEOUS WOMAN!
- YEAH.
- I FELT LIKE ANGELIC.
I JUST FELT LIKE REALLY,
REALLY PRETTY.
AND I FEEL LIKE ONCE YOU FEEL
REALLY REALLY PRETTY IN A DRESS,
THAT'S YOUR DRESS!
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
- THIS IS, LIKE, MY DRESS.
- THAT'S YOUR WEDDING DRESS.
- DO YOU LIKE IT ON ME?
- I LOVE IT.
IT'S GORGEOUS.
- THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT
YOU WOULD BE WEARING,
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- WOW.
I HAVE MY BUTTERFLIES.
- DO YOU?
[gasps]
YOU WANNA GET MARRIED?
NO?
OH, YOU WANNA GET MARRIED.
ARE YOU GONNA CRY?
- HUH? NO.
- ARE YOU GONNA CRY? OH.
- NOT GONNA CRY.
I AM LIKE HOLY [bleep].
LIKE, THIS ACTUALLY MIGHT BE
SOMETHING I WANT.
YOU KNOW, IT'S SCARY.
'CAUSE ME AND ROGER AGREED
THAT THIS ISN'T GONNA HAPPEN
ANYTIME SOON.
AND LOOK AT ME,
I'M TRYING ON WEDDING DRESSES.
AND I'M LIKE, OOH!
NOW I WANNA GET MARRIED
SO I CAN BE IN THE DRESS
OF MY DREAMS FOR A DAY
AND FEEL LIKE THIS PRINCESS.
- THAT MAKES ME HAPPY FOR HER.
- THANKS.
- WE'RE IN [bleep]
WEDDING DRESSES.
WHAT THE [bleep] GOING ON?
- I HAVE NO IDEA.
- I'M GONNA BE A BRIDE.
- YOU...LOOK...PERFECT.
- MM, MM.
WHAT DO YOU DO
IF YOU GOTTA PEE?
- I THINK YOU MAKE SURE YOU PEE.
- WHAT IF I GET DRUNK?
PEEL OFF MY DRESS.
- THERE'S MORE SNOOKI AND JWOWW
ON THE WAY.
- AND IT CONTINUES NOW.
I'M BUYING THE DRESS!
- OH, MY GOD!
- YAY!
- I'M GETTIN' MARRIED.
I WAS NOT EXPECTING
TO GO TO THIS PLACE
AND FIND A WEDDING DRESS.
IT WAS MORE OF LIKE
TO HAVE FUN WITH MY BOO,
SO IT'S CRAZY
THAT I FOUND IT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I FOUND MY DRESS.
- IT WAS OUR PLEASURE.
CONGRATULATIONS.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- YOU'RE WELCOME.
TAKE CARE.
- I THINK I RIPPED
LIKE THREE DRESSES.
[laughter]
BUT I GAVE THEM
YOUR CREDIT CARD INFORMATION,
SO IT SHOULD BE FINE.
- OH, THAT'S FABULOUS.
- * I DON'T WANNA STAY
THIS WAY FOREVER *
* ARE YOU READY TO...
- OPEN YOUR EYES!
- [laughing]
HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
DID YOU FIND
WHAT YOU WERE LOOKING FOR?
- I FOUND MY DRESS.
- OH, I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE HER.
I'M SO GLAD THAT YOU FOUND IT.
THAT'S THE FIRST STEP.
- AND I FEEL LIKE A PRINCESS.
- YOU'RE GONNA LOOK LIKE ONE.
- MM.
OH, THE JOEYS CAME.
- OH, MY GOD.
- MY JOEY TRIED ON A DRESS.
- DID BEAR?
- YEAH.
HE LOOKED LIKE THE FAT GIRL
AT PROM.
- WITH THAT BEARD?
- YES.
- THAT SOUNDS REALLY GAY.
- IT WAS.
- [laughing]
- IT WAS VERY GAY.
JENNI TRIED ON
THE DRESSES TOO.
- JENNI TRIED ON DRESSES?
- YEAH.
SHE WANTS TO GET MARRIED NOW,
BUT SHE'S SCARED TO TELL ROGER
BECAUSE SHE DOESN'T KNOW
HOW ROGER'S GONNA REACT.
SO NOW JENNI WANTS TO PLAN
A WEDDING I THINK.
- I WANNA BE AT THAT WEDDING.
[laughs]
- THEY NEED JESUS.
I FEEL LIKE JENNI DOES
WANNA GET MARRIED,
BUT THEN LIKE THE NEXT DAY
SHE DOESN'T.
I MEAN, SHE JUST ALWAYS
CHANGES HER MIND.
- IT'S NOT SOMETHING
YOU CAN BE CONFUSED ABOUT.
YOU EITHER WANNA DO IT
OR YOU DON'T.
- AND I WANNA MARRY YOU.
- ME TOO.
WELL, YOU.
OOH!
WE'RE GETTING MARRIED!
- LET'S GO WAKE UP
THE DADDY.
I'M IN A VERY PSYCHEDELIC STAGE
RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE I DON'T WANNA
GET MARRIED,
BUT NOW I WANNA GET MARRIED.
SO YEAH, TWILIGHT ZONE.
- YOU HAVE FUN?
- UM, IT WENT
LIKE I DIDN'T EXPECT IT TO GO.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- [whispering]
I TRIED ON DRESSES.
- REALLY.
- IT WAS LIKE...
- FELT LIKE A PRINCESS?
- YEAH.
- [laughing]
- WHAT?
- YOU'RE OKAY.
YOU CAN FEEL LIKE A PRINCESS.
I FELT PRETTY...
IN ALL THE DRESSES.
- YOU ARE PRETTY.
YOU ARE PRETTY.
MY LITTLE PRINCESS.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
IT MADE YOU FEEL LIKE YOU WANNA
GET MARRIED NOW YOU MEAN?
- MAYBE.
- I'M PLEASANTLY SURPRISED.
AND I'M EXCITED ABOUT IT.
I JUST WANT THE BEST FOR US,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I WANT YOU TO HAVE
THAT MOMENT.
I HOPE THAT WHAT WE'RE DOING
WITH THERAPY
AND WITH OUR RELATIONSHIP
GETS US THERE ONE DAY.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT I WANT,
BUT I WANT YOU TO SUPPORT
WHAT I WANT.
THAT'S ALL.
- I DO SUPPORT WHAT YOU WANT.
- IT'S GREAT THAT ROGER FEELS
THE WAY THAT HE DOES.
HE HAS MY FULL SUPPORT,
COMING HOME AND FEELING
THE WAY THAT I DO RIGHT
- YOU HAVE MY FULL SUPPORT
YOU MEAN.
- HUH?
- YOU SAID
"HE HAS MY FULL SUPPORT."
YOU HAVE MY FULL SUPPORT
YOU MEANT TO SAY, RIGHT?
I WOULD LOVE TO MAKE YOU
A BEAUTIFUL PRINCESS ONE DAY.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT MAYBE NEXT YEAR?
- I THINK THAT'S
A DEFINITE POSSIBILITY, YEAH.
- I'M SO GLAD
THAT ROGER'S SUPPORTING ME.
NO, I DID IT WRONG AGAIN?
I [bleep] DON'T KNOW.
- JUST HIT IT AGAIN.
- I DON'T WANT SUPPORT ANYMORE
IN THIS [bleep] CONVERSATION.
- YOU SOUND LIKE
YOU HAD A GREAT NIGHT.
- I DID.
I ALMOST CRIED WHEN I SAW HER.
- THE MOOD IS GOOD RIGHT NOW,
YOU KNOW?
MAYBE IT'S SETTING THE TONE
FOR THE REST OF THE NIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, BABE?
- I HAVE GAS.
- OKAY.
- BABE, I'M DISABLED.
I HAVE A BAD INJURY.
- ALL RIGHT, I'M NOT GONNA RUIN
THIS BEAUTIFUL NIGHT
BY HUMPING YOU.
- THANK YOU.
- IS THIS THE FRONT DOOR?
- YEAH, THIS IS
YOUR FRONT ENTRANCE.
- WE'RE BUILDING A HOUSE.
WE CAN DESIGN IT
HOWEVER WE WANT.
- [screams]
- I'M NERVOUS.
- LET'S GO ADOPT A BABY.
WE'RE NOT PARENTS,
WE'VE NEVER ADOPTED A CHILD.
- I WOULD LOVE TO GIVE A CHILD
THAT SAME LOVE AND CARE THAT,
YOU KNOW, MY BEST FRIEND
AND I HAVE.
- HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT
THE TYPE OF CEREMONY?
- I'M SO CONFUSED.
- [laughing]
- WE HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT WE'RE DOING.