- MY FAVORITE DRESS
I'M FINALLY TRYING ON,
AND I HAVE GOOSE BUMPS.
- DO YOU? [gasps]
YOU WANT TO GET MARRIED?
NO?
OH, YOU WANT TO GET MARRIED.
ARE YOU GONNA CRY?
- ROGER'S GONNA KILL ME.
- I KNOW THAT I NEED
TO WORK ON ROMANCE.
I KNOW THAT, BUT I JUST
WOULD LIKE TO WALK IN THE ROOM
AND PULL JENNI'S SKIRT DOWN
AND RAVAGE HER.
- UGH.
- I FEEL LIKE
SINCE I'M FROM CHILE,
I FEEL LIKE I AM CHILEAN...
- YEAH.
- BUT, I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW,
SO I'M GONNA GET A DNA TEST.
[Icona Pop's I Love It]
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* *
* I DON'T CARE *
- * BA BA BA-DA-DA-DA
WHAT DO YOU SAY? *
- MOMMY IS GONNA GO
FIND OUT WHAT SHE IS TODAY.
[Lorenzo yells]
SHE IS--
YOU DON'T WANT ME TO GO?
SINCE I'M ADOPTED,
I REALLY WANT TO GET A DNA TEST.
I WOULD LIKE TO KNOW WHAT I AM,
SO I CAN TELL MY SON
ONE DAY WHAT HE IS.
YOU READY TO FIND OUT
WHAT WE ARE?
IF WE'RE ALIENS
OR WEIRDOS
OR A SPIDER?
IMAGINE IF WE WERE
LIKE SPIDER-MAN.
[Lorenzo laughs]
COULD BE DIFFERENT THINGS,
WHICH IS COOL.
WHEN I WAS GROWING UP, I GOOGLED
WHAT CHILEAN PEOPLE LOOK LIKE,
AND THEY ALL LOOK LIKE ME.
LIKE, LITTLE [bleep]
SHORT [bleep] WALKING AROUND.
IT'S NOT BLOOD WORK, RIGHT?
- NO BLOOD WORK.
[laughs] SO RELAX.
- IT DOESN'T HURT?
- IT DOESN'T HURT.
- OKAY.
- WE'RE GOING TO BE LOOKING
FOR NATIVE AMERICAN ONE,
NATIVE AMERICAN TWO,
JEWISH ONE, JEWISH TWO,
JEWISH THREE,
AND JEWISH FOUR.
- YOU CAN TELL IF YOU'RE JEWISH?
- MM-HMM.
- HOW DO YOU FIND OUT
IF YOU'RE JEWISH?
I FEEL LIKE
THAT'S, LIKE, A RELIGION,
AND YOU PICK
WHAT YOU BELIEVE IN,
SO I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE BORN, LIKE, JEWISH.
I'M NOT JEWISH.
I'M CHRISTIAN.
CATHOLIC?
ARE THEY THE SAME THINGS?
I'M CATHOLIC.
THERE'S A POSSIBILITY THAT
I COULD BE FROM ANOTHER PLANET,
LIKE I'M AN ALIEN.
- WELL, YOU COULD ALWAYS BE
FROM MARS, WE NEVER KNOW.
MAYBE WE'LL FIND OUT.
- I FEEL LIKE I'M AN ALIEN.
- SOMETIMES, WE ALL FEEL
LIKE WE'RE ALIENS.
[laughs]
- YEAH.
- OKAY, OPEN UP.
[Lorenzo babbling]
- WOULD YOU TELL THE FBI,
THEN THEY WOULD TAKE ME AWAY,
OR WOULD YOU JUST
LET ME LIVE?
I MEAN,
I WATCH A LOT OF MOVIES,
AND THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS.
PEOPLE DON'T KNOW
THEY'RE ALIENS,
THEY FIND OUT THEY'RE ALIENS,
AND THE GOVERNMENT
JUST ANAL-PROBES YOU.
- PROMISE YOU,
THEY'RE NOT GONNA FIND OUT.
[laughs]
- * BROTHER, HEAR ME NOW,
IT'S NOT OUR TOWN *
- SO BRING ME UP TO DATE.
WHERE DO WE STAND ON INTIMACY?
I LIKE THE TERM "MAKING LOVE."
- MAKING--I DO TOO.
- EW.
- IT'S THE PROCESS THAT CAN
CONSUMMATE IN THE SEXUAL ACT,
BUT YOU GO THROUGH THE KISSING,
TAKING IT SLOW TO TOUCHING.
- CARESSING.
GENTLE CARESSES.
- THE WHOLE CARESSING
AND EVERYTHING
IS REALLY WEIRD FOR ME,
I'M GONNA BE HONEST.
- BUT IT IS--THAT IS PASSION.
THAT IS--
- BUT YOU JUST LOOK LIKE
A PERVERT.
- HOW ELSE WOULD I DO IT?
- I FELT LIKE
AN OLD MAN IS TOUCHING ME.
- HOW WOULD YOU LIKE ME
TO SHOW YOU AFFECTION?
- I JUST WANT YOU TO GIVE ME
MORE HUGS AND KISSES,
FLOWERS,
BE MORE "ATTENTATIVE,"
PLAY WITH OUR DOGS MORE.
- "ATTENTATIVE"?
- ATTENTIVE, SHE MEANT.
- ATTENTIVE.
LIKE, I'M NERVOUS NOW.
YOU MADE ME--
I'M CLAMMY RIGHT NOW.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO HAVE SEX
WITH ME FOUR TIMES A DAY.
HOW ABOUT ONCE A WEEK?
- NO.
- AND THAT'S FINE...
- WHEN IS THAT FINE?
- BUT IF YOU ACTUALLY KISSED ME
AND HUGGED ME
AND DONE NICE THINGS FOR ME
AND TO BE, LIKE--
AND JUST A PECK, LIKE...
[kisses]
"HOW WAS WORK?
OKAY, BYE, I'M GONE."
THIS DOES NOT MEAN
YOU GET LAID RIGHT NOW.
- [whistles] NO?
I NEED TO KNOW ON MY END,
THOUGH,
THAT, LIKE, YOUR LOINS
STILL BURN AND YEARN FOR ME.
- CAN YOU N--
SEE, THIS IS--
YOU DON'T KNOW ROGER
WHERE I KNOW HIM.
LOOK AT HIS SMIRK.
- NO, I'M NOT--YOU'RE SMIRKING.
- BABE? B--YES.
BECAUSE YOU'RE MAKING IT
VERY UNCOMFORTABLE IN HERE.
- NO, I'M TAKING THIS
VERY SERIOUS.
THIS IS OUR LIVES,
AND I WANT THE PASSION BACK.
- THAT HAS TO BE APPROACHED
BY MAKING HER FEEL COMFORTABLE,
MAKING HER FEEL LOVED,
MAKING HER FEEL SPECIAL.
- EXACTLY,
LIKE A KOALA IN A ZOO.
- [laughs]
- YOU'RE MAKING THIS SO AWKWARD.
- NO, YOU HAVE TO--
- [laughs]
- AND YOU NEED TO JUST
SHUT YOUR MOUTH.
- THIS IS VIOLENCE!
THIS IS SETTING US BACK!
- GUYS, OKAY.
- IT'S SETTING US BACK MILES.
SHE HURTS ME, DOCTOR.
- HE DOESN'T REALIZE
THAT I'M DOING THIS OUT OF LOVE.
- I'M DYING.
OW, AH! THAT HURT.
IT--SHE HURTS ME.
[grunts]
- SO THIS CAN'T BE PUSHED
AND RUSHED AT THIS POINT.
SHE'S LOOKING FOR AFFECTION.
- AFFECTION.
- MAYBE SOME MASSAGING.
- YES.
MAYBE A HOT OIL MASSAGE
TONIGHT WOULD BE A GOOD--
- NO.
- THINK WE'VE LOST
SOME OF THE ATMOSPHERE
FOR TONIGHT.
- YEAH.
- POSSIBLY TOMORROW?
I THINK MY INTIMACY
COMES ACROSS AS A JOKE
BECAUSE I HAVEN'T BEEN
A ROMANTIC GUY.
DEFINITELY THINKING
WHAT I NEED TO DO RIGHT NOW
TO BRING THAT SPARK AND THAT
ROMANCE BACK TO MY RELATIONSHIP
IS TO SPICE THINGS UP,
TO MAKE JENNI FEEL BEAUTIFUL,
AND TO BE
A BEAUTIFUL PRINCESS.
- AND WE'LL GET TOGETHER
AGAIN SOON.
- YES.
- THANK YOU.
- GREAT TO SEE YOU.
- CLOTHES ON OR CLOTHES OFF
NEXT TIME?
- [scoffs] I'M--
- WHAT?
[phone ringing]
- YO!
MY MAN, WHAT'S UP?
- SO YOU KNOW
HOW WE'RE IN THERAPY.
MY LAST SESSION,
BASICALLY, WE KIND OF HAD
A LITTLE BIT OF A BREAKTHROUGH
THAT I NEED TO BE MORE ROMANTIC
IN THE RELATIONSHIP,
SO I WAS THINKING
ABOUT TRYING TO COOK HER DINNER.
CAN YOU HELP ME?
- I'LL DO ANYTHING TO HELP YOU,
MY FRIEND.
MAKE IT
A LITTLE DOUBLE DATE.
- ALL RIGHT, BUDDY.
I APPRECIATE IT.
- YOU GOT IT, PAL.
I'LL TALK TO YOU.
- I'M TRYING TO PAY ATTENTION
TO WHAT I'M LEARNING IN THERAPY.
I'VE NEVER, LIKE, MADE A MEAL
FROM SCRATCH FOR JENNI,
AND, YOU KNOW,
I THINK IT'S TIME.
[exhales]
LET'S DO THIS.
[phone ringing]
- HEY, HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I JUST GOT BACK
FROM DOGGY DAY CARE,
AND, OH, MY GOD,
I SAW THE CUTEST FLYER THERE.
IT'S, LIKE, A DOGGY
CHARITY WASH OUTSIDE,
AND IT'S FOR TOMS RIVER
ANIMAL SHELTER,
SO IT'S LIKE
ALL THE DONATIONS GO THERE.
I DIDN'T KNOW IF YOU WOULD BE
DOWN TO, LIKE, WASH DOGS.
- I'M DOWN.
YOU KNOW I LOVE DOGGIES.
I'LL MAKE SOME SIGNS FOR US.
- YAY.
YAY!
FUND-RAISER, CHARITY.
- WOOF, WOOF, WOOF.
- ME AND YOU ARE ALWAYS
GIVING BACK,
SO I FEEL LIKE THIS IS AWESOME,
AND WE GET TO WASH DOGS.
- I LOVE ANIMALS,
MORE THAN PEOPLE.
- ME TOO.
- LOVE 'EM.
- I [bleep] HATE PEOPLE.
- MM-HMM.
- I'M "DOG," YOU'RE "WASH."
- IS THIS GOOD?
- DOG WASH, DOG WASH.
LET'S PUT IT UPSIDE DOWN,
SO IT'S FUNNY.
DOG W--[laughs]
- ONLY YOU WOULD PUT THE WASH
UPSIDE DOWN.
- I MEAN, PEOPLE GET THE IDEA.
THEY KNOW WHAT WE'RE DOING.
DOG WASH.
SHOW SOME [bleep].
WHOO! DOG WASH!
- THAT'S WHY I CUT THE HOLE.
- EW.
- LET'S GO WASH.
- OKAY.
I WOULD LIKE TO TAKE
THE SMALL DOGS,
BECAUSE I'M NOT REALLY
COMFORTABLE WITH THE LARGE DOGS,
SO I'LL DO THE SMALL.
- I DON'T MIND.
- YOU CAN DO THE LARGE.
- COME HERE, CHUBBY CHUBBIES.
COME HERE, CHUBBY.
- OH, LITTLE PUPPIES.
- AW, JUST DON'T FART.
- THERE YOU GO.
- [chuckles]
both: OH!
- [screams]
- THERE GOES AN EYELASH.
[laughter]
THEY DON'T HAVE AN EXTENSION
CORD WITH A BLOW DRYER?
AW, YOU GOT GOOD HAIR.
- THIS IS REALLY NICE HAIR.
- I WONDER IF THEY SELL
DOG HAIR IN WEAVE.
WANT TO DO A BOW? HERE.
- IT'S A BOY, IT'S A BOY.
- OH, IT'S A BOY?
- WHOOPSIE.
YOU THINK
WE WOULD'VE SAW A WIENER.
- TODAY,
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU
A RECIPE
FROM THE SOUTHWEST OF FRANCE.
- JENNI SAYS
THAT IF I'M MORE ROMANTIC,
SHE'LL HAVE MORE SEX WITH ME,
SO I'M GONNA STEP UP.
I'M GONNA START BEING
MORE ROMANTIC,
AND I WANT TO COOK
A NICE DINNER FOR JENNI.
- IT'S GONNA BE
THE CHICKEN BASQUAISE.
- HOW DO YOU SPELL "PASQUEZ"?
- PAS...QUEZ.
[laughter]
- P-A-S-QUEZ.
- [laughs]
- WE'RE GONNA USE ONE CHICKEN
FOR, LIKE, FOUR PEOPLE.
- HE GOES, "SHE-CAN."
- "SHE-CAN."
- THREE NICE SLICE OF BACON.
- "BEE-CAN."
- [laughs] OF "BEACON."
- A LITTLE BIT OF,
LIKE, PAPRIKA.
- I THOUGHT HE SAID
"A HEFTY PAP--"
- HE SAID A WHAT?
- I CAN'T UNDERSTAND ANYTHING
THIS GUY'S SAYING.
- [speaking indistinctly]
SOUFFLE AU CHOCOLAT.
- WHAT?
[laughs]
- ADD A LITTLE WHITE WINE.
- LITTLE WHITE WINE.
WOW.
- "A LITTLE WHITE WINE,"
HE SAID, RIGHT?
- YEAH.
HATE TO SEE HOW MUCH WE PUT IN.
- YEAH,
GET THESE GIRLS LOADED.
- HEY, YOU WANT TO GET LUCKY
OR WHAT? COME ON.
- [laughs] THAT'S THE ONLY WAY
I'M GONNA GET LUCKY.
- GET TWO BOTTLES.
[indie rock music]
* *
- OOH!
- [bleep]!
- [bleep] DON'T EVEN PLAY
THAT GAME WITH ME!
- [laughs] [bleep].
[laughs] OH, MY--
- YOU GOTTA COME OUT
SOMETIME.
- TRUCE?
- THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT,
[bleep].
[burps]
- HI, CLYDE!
- HI, JENNI.
- HI, IZ!
- COME ON, BUBBA.
- DO YOU STILL LIKE US
AFTER THAT WHOLE CAKE [bleep]?
[screams]
- OH, THAT WAS NOTHING.
- WE REALLY [bleep] UP.
- [shushes]
- [laughs]
- OOH, I MEAN,
DON'T SAY THAT WORD EVER.
I'M A NEW MOM,
AND I STILL [bleep] SWEAR.
- YOU GOT TO TEACH HER,
'CAUSE LORENZO'S GONNA BE
THEIR AGE SOON.
- I'M GONNA BE
THE WORST PARENT EVER.
- [laughs]
- IT IS WHAT IT IS.
I'M HUMAN,
AND SOMETIMES I SWEAR.
[bleep] IT.
- SHE GOT HIM AT THE RESCUE.
- IS THAT A PIT BULL?
- YEAH. HIM AND LOUIE...
- WOW.
- WHICH IS A CHIHUAHUA.
- AREN'T CHIHUAHUAS [bleep]?
[laughter]
OH.
DO NOT SAY THAT WORD.
SWEARING, IT'S HOW
YOU EXPRESS YOURSELF.
- YEAH.
- SO YOU CAN SAY [bleep],
IT'S FINE.
- SO AS LONG AS IT'S NOT, LIKE,
"[bleep] YOU IN YOUR FACE."
- YEAH.
OR "I WILL [bleep] ON YOU."
- IT'S FINE.
- BUT IF IT'S LIKE, [bleep]...
both: IT'S FINE.
- ALL RIGHT, THAT'S ENOUGH.
- ALL RIGHT.
- I JUST NEED
TO STOP SPEAKING.
I'M A MESS, I NEED TO GO HOME.
- WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO HAVE
AN ETIQUETTE LESSON.
- I GOT TO GO HOME.
- SWEARING
IN FRONT OF THE KIDS.
[laughter]
- SORRY.
[bleep].
- IF ONE WAS LOOKING
FOR A WHOLE CHICKEN,
WHERE WOULD I FIND IT?
- MAYBE IN AISLE ONE--
OR I MEAN TWO?
- AISLE TWO? ALL RIGHT.
- WE DON'T GROCERY SHOP. I MEAN,
I GO WITH JENNI ONCE IN A WHILE,
BUT I JUST BASICALLY JUST
ZONE OUT, AND I PUSH THE CART.
YOU KNOW, AND WE ACTUALLY
HAVE TO FIND STUFF NOW,
LIKE, REAL INGREDIENTS.
- WHAT'S THE OTHER STUFF
HE SAID?
KULMER? KALMER?
- OH, NO, UH--
- KALMER? KEEMER?
WE CAN'T EVEN SAY THE THINGS.
HOW ARE WE GONNA BUY THEM?
HI, HOW ARE YOU?
- OOPS, EXCUSE ME.
- GREAT.
I WENT TO HIGH SCHOOL WITH HER.
[both chuckling]
- WHAT DID YOU SAY, UNSWEETENED?
- UNSWEETENED CHOCOLATE.
NO, BITTERSWEET CHOCOLATE,
SORRY, BITTERSWEET.
- BITTER.
- DID WE JUST HEAR
THAT GUY WRONG?
MAYBE IT'S SEMISWEET.
- OH, [bleep],
WAS IT BITTERSWEET OR SEMI--
WAS IT SEMISWEET?
WHAT DID HE SAY?
BITTERSWEET OR WHAT?
- I DON'T KNOW
WHERE YOU'RE GOING.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
"QUIMOA."
MAYBE WE CAN FIND "QUIMOA"
DOWN HERE.
- I STILL DON'T KNOW
WHO "QUIMOA" IS.
- SEE "QUIMOA" ANYWHERE?
- IS THIS A SICK JOKE?
- COMES IN BOXES.
I DON'T SEE IT,
AND USUALLY,
"QUIMOA" IS RIGHT HERE.
THIS IS NOT "QUIMOA."
NONE OF THAT IS "QUIMOA."
- I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT "QUIMOA" IS.
WHAT THE [bleep] IS IT?
[grunts]
- PICK THAT UP.
YO, FIX YOUR MESS.
WHERE YOU GOING?
- SIR, "QUIMOA,"
WHERE WOULD WE FIND THAT?
- HUH?
- "QUIMOA."
- WHO?
- DO YOU WORK HERE?
- YEAH, I DO WORK HERE.
- [laughs]
- "QUIMOA"?
[Too Old by Swimm]
* *
- ALL RIGHT,
SO I WOULD SAY
WE START WITH CUTTING
THE CHICKEN UP, RIGHT?
- NO.
- NO?
- GOT TO WATCH THE VIDEO.
HERE WE GO.
- WE JUST GOT BACK TO THE HOUSE.
TIME IS OF THE ESSENCE.
WE REALLY DON'T KNOW WHEN
THE GIRLS ARE GOING TO BE HOME.
TIME TO COOK, MAN.
YOU READY?
- LET'S DO THIS.
[indistinct chatter]
- OH, THERE WAS
SOMETHING HE JUST SAID.
I DIDN'T HEAR WHAT HE JUST SAID.
- REWIND.
- I CAN'T UNDERSTAND
THIS FRENCHMAN.
- YO, YOU EVER CUT A CHICKEN
BEFORE?
- LET ME SEE.
THE BACKBONE.
- THE BACKBONE WOULD BE
RIGHT HERE, CORRECT?
- LET ME SEE, LET ME SEE,
LET ME SEE.
- THAT'S THE BACK.
THIS IS THE LEG COMING THIS WAY.
- YEAH, YOU'RE GOOD, YEAH.
STRAIGHT DOWN THE MIDDLE.
- THAT'S ALL BONE, DUDE.
- YEAH, CUT IT THROUGH--
THE CLOSEST
TO THE RIGHT OF IT,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- RIGHT.
- SO YOU PRETTY MUCH FOLLOW
THE BACKBONE.
- FOLLOW THE BACKBONE.
NICE, OH, THAT'S A GOOD CUT.
THAT IS A GOOD CUT.
- NOW I KNOW
WHY I NEVER TOOK UP COOKING.
- UGH.
[grunts]
[straining]
JENNI! JENNI!
[laughs]
- HOLD ON.
- I NEED HELP.
- YOU GOT TO LEARN
HOW TO DO THAT FOR LORENZO.
- [scoffs] THAT'S NOT MY JOB,
IT'S JIONNI'S JOB.
[air horn blares]
- [laughs]
- WHAT THE [bleep] WAS THAT?
- MAKING SURE YOU'RE AWAKE,
BUDDY.
- WHAT ARE YOU, SIX?
- [laughs]
- YOU JUMPED
SO [bleep] BAD, DUDE.
EH, IT WAS AWESOME.
JIONNI'S ON THE STOVE,
HE'S COOKING.
I MIGHT AS WELL TAKE
THIS OPPORTUNITY TO GO IN
AND SET UP THE DINING ROOM.
GET THE BALLOONS OUT,
GET THE ROSE PETALS OUT,
GET THE FLOWERS SET UP,
GET THE CANDLES SET UP
TO KIND OF SET THE AMBIANCE.
- WHY DON'T WE START
THE SOUFFLE?
- YES, LET'S DO THAT.
- FOR DESSERT, WE'RE GONNA MAKE
A SOUFFLE AU CHOCOLAT.
- FRERE JACQUES!
- * FRERE JACQUES,
FRERE JACQUES *
GOT TO GO IN THE CENTER
OF THE DISH.
- OKAY.
I'M SOUFFLE-ING TONIGHT.
AFTER I COOK THE SOUFFLE,
I'M SOUFFLE-ING MYSELF.
- I HAVE VERY, VERY,
VERY LITTLE HOPE
OF GETTING SOUFFLE TONIGHT.
- AFTER THIS AWESOME MEAL?
- VERY LITTLE.
- ROG.
DO I HAVE TO TALK TO JENNI?
- YOU NEED TO TALK TO HER.
- [scoffs] YOU DON'T GET LAID
AFTER THIS NIGHT,
FORGET ABOUT IT.
[indie rock music]
- * OH, OH, OH *
* YOUR HEART SLOWS DOWN *
- WE'RE HOME.
- UGH, GOD, I SMELL.
- YEAH, THE--
IT WAS THE MIDDLE.
- BABE,
I GOT NICOLE WITH ME.
- THEY HERE?
- IT SMELLS LIKE SAUSAGE--
- OH, MY GOD!
- SURPRISE!
- OH, MY GOD, LOOK AT YOU!
JIONNI, YOU'RE HERE?
- DIESEL.
- [laughs]
- BABE?
- WHAT'S UP, MAMA?
- OH!
- I CAN'T KISS YOU
TILL YOU PUT THAT KILLER DOWN.
- NO, SHE--
YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU ALL DAY.
- [sniffs]
[crying] YOU'RE SO SWEET!
- AW.
- OH, SHE'S CRYING.
- [sighs]
- WHY ARE YOU CRYING?
- HOW COME YOU DON'T GET
EMOTIONAL LIKE THAT?
[laughs]
JIONNI AND I ARE BOTH
IN THE KITCHEN.
NICOLE IS FIRST
THROUGH THE ENTRYWAY, AND--
- MELTS IN MY ARMS.
- IMMEDIATELY STARTS BAWLING,
TELLING HER MAN HOW MUCH
SHE LOVES HIM, AND MY GIRL--
- SHE SAID, "WHAT'S UP, BRO?"
- "WHAT'S UP, DOG?"
[laughter]
- THAT'S SWEET.
- LIKE, THIS WAS MY IDEA.
- IT WAS HIS--
IT WAS YOUR IDEA TOO.
OH, MY GOD, WAS SHE--
- AND MY THERAPIST SAYS
THAT I NEED TO BE ROMANTIC.
- OH, MY GOD.
- WE'RE GONNA GET CHANGED,
SO WE DON'T STINK.
- OKAY. FIRST COURSE
IS IN ABOUT TEN MINUTES.
- FIRST COURSE?
- YUP, FIRST COURSE
IS TEN MINUTES.
- FIRST COURSE.
- I LOVE YOU GUYS.
- BE PREPARED, LADIES.
- OH!
- WE'VE BEEN WORKING HARD.
- YOU KNOW, WHEY GUYS WANT
TO SHOW THEIR APPRECIATION
FOR THEIR WOMEN,
THIS IS WHAT THEY DO.
AND I LOVE IT.
- ONCE IN A BLUE MOON,
BUT, MAN, WHEN YOU GET IT,
LIKE, THEY O.D. ON IT.
- YOU--YEAH.
- FIRST COURSE, I'M JUST GONNA
WALK IN, HAND IT TO 'EM.
- WELL, WE GOT TO SAY,
"POULET CHICKEN BASQUAISE."
- "CHICKEN BASQUAISE."
- OKAY, WE'LL SAY,
"CHICKEN POULET BASQUAISE."
- NO, THAT WOULD BE
"CHICKEN CHICKEN," IDIOT.
[horn blares]
- DOES THAT MEAN DINNER?
IS THAT OUR COW BELL?
THIS DEFINITELY MAKES ME WANT TO
DO SOMETHING SWEET FOR JIONNI,
SO WHEN WE GET BACK HOME,
YOU KNOW, WE'LL PROBABLY DO
A LITTLE KISS, KISS.
- DINNER IS SERVED.
- THIS IS A--
- OH, MY GOD.
- THIS IS
A BEAUTIFUL FRENCH DISH.
- FRENCH DINNER.
WE CALL IT
"CHICKEN POULET BASQUAISE."
- "POULET BASQUAISE."
- [laughs]
- IT'S FRENCH.
WE'VE NEVER MADE IT BEFORE,
BUT--
- IT'S PRETTY.
- YES, ENJOY.
- BABE, I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
- BON APPETIT.
- I'M PROUD OF BOTH OF YOU.
- ENJOY.
- I'M SO PROUD OF YOU GUYS.
- THAT'S AMAZING.
- LOOK AT NICOLE.
OH, MY GOD.
- [laughs]
- THIS SMELLS, LIKE,
REALLY GOOD.
I LOVE IT.
- IT'S AN ORGANIC CHICKEN.
- I DON'T THINK IT'S THAT BAD.
- I ACTUALLY THINK IT'S GOOD.
- I THINK IT'S DELICIOUS.
- CHICKEN'S A LITTLE DRY,
MAYBE A LITTLE TOO LONG, BUT--
- I DON'T EVEN THINK
IT'S DRY AT ALL.
- IT'S NOT DRY AT ALL.
- IT'S SO GOOD.
- IT WAS PERFECT.
- IT'S GOOD?
- MM-HMM.
- WHOSE IDEA WAS THIS?
- YEAH.
- IT WAS MORE--
ROGER WAS DOING IT FOR JENNI.
HE WAS, BUT THEN HE SAID--
- AW!
- OH, THANKS, BABY.
- HE WAS.
- I INVITED JIONNI TO COME OVER
AND GIVE ME A HAND,
BECAUSE HE'S A LITTLE BIT
BETTER, YOU KNOW, COOK.
- THEN HE SAID,
"CAN YOU HELP ME?
'CAUSE I KNOW
THEY'LL BE TOGETHER," SO...
- SO THERAPY'S WORKING?
- YES.
- THAT'S AWESOME.
- WELL, THE SURPRISE ISN'T OVER.
WE HAVE DESSERT RIGHT NOW.
- FOR DESSERT, WE HAVE
THE CHOCOLAT AU SOUFFLE.
JIONNI, COME HERE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- GOOD.
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA EAT
FOR DESSERT?
- I DON'T NEED ONE.
- [laughs]
- WE'LL SPLIT IT, NO.
- WE HAD--
WE HAD FOUR...
- NO, I KNOW.
- ALL SITTING HERE TOGETHER.
- YOU COULD--
- WHY DID YOU LEAVE
THIS ONE OUT?
- 'CAUSE THE GUY WANTED IT
IN THE MIDDLE.
- DOESN'T MATTER.
THEY WOULD HAVE FIT.
IT'S STILL IN THE MIDDLE.
YOU [bleep] UP,
AND YOU'RE LYING.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN I'M LYING?
- ADMIT YOU [bleep] UP.
- I PUT IT IN THE MIDDLE.
- YOU [bleep] UP.
YOU FORGOT ONE.
- IT'S FINE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
- [laughs]
- THERE'S MORE SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW
ON THE WAY.
- AND IT CONTINUES NOW.
- * NOBODY LIKES A SAD SONG *
- YOU [bleep] UP,
AND YOU'RE LYING.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN, I'M LYING?
- ADMIT YOU [bleep] UP.
- I PUT IT IN THE MIDDLE.
- YOU [bleep] UP.
YOU FORGOT ONE.
- I KNOW THERE'S FOUR OF US,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
ROGER,
YOU CAN HAVE MY SOUFFLE.
I'M GETTING MY SOUFFLE
BACK AT THE HOUSE.
NOW, LADIES, THIS IS
THE SOUFFLE "CHOC-LETTE."
NOW, I'VE NEVER MADE
A DESSERT BEFORE.
- WE CAN SHARE, LITTLE BUDDY,
'CAUSE WE--
- YEAH, I'M NOT GONNA EAT--
TRUST ME.
- NO, I'LL HAVE A LITTLE BIT
OF IT WITH YOU, AND THEN,
WHEN THE OTHER ONE'S DONE--
- WHY?
- 'CAUSE I-I--
- NO, I'M REALLY FULL.
I'LL WAIT FOR YOU.
- YOU ONLY COULD FIT THREE
IN THE PAN,
AND I PUT THREE IN.
THERE'S FOUR OF US.
- THAT'S FINE, I'LL WAIT.
- YOU COULD HAVE FIT,
LIKE, EIGHT IN THE PAN.
- YOU TOLD ME TO PUT 'EM
IN THE MIDDLE.
- RIGHT, BUT THERE WAS
PLENTY OF ROOM FOR IT TO GO
IN THE MIDDLE, YOU [bleep].
- NO, THERE WASN'T.
- YES, THERE WAS.
OH, MAN.
- NAILED IT.
- IT'S GOOD?
- IT'S HOT.
- NAILED IT.
- NO, HE'S GONNA SPLIT MINE.
- AH, [bleep].
[laughter]
- WHAT--
- YOU PUT IT IN THE OIL DISH,
YOU--[laughs]
- HOW DID YOU MAKE THIS?
- IT'S [bleep] AWESOME.
- YOU MADE THIS?
- TASTE THAT.
- WE BOTH MADE IT.
- I DID.
- I'M MORE PROUD,
I'M MORE HAPPY ABOUT THIS.
- EVERYTHING ON THIS TABLE...
- HOW'D YOU MAKE IT?
- IT WAS A COMBINED EFFORT.
IT REALLY WAS.
- WE REALLY CAN'T TELL YOU,
JUST IN CASE
WE WANT TO SURPRISE YOU AGAIN.
- BABE, NO SECRETS.
- JIONNI, I WILL COOK WITH YOU
ANY DAY, SIR, ANY DAY.
- I FEEL LIKE YOU GUYS HAVE MORE
FUN WHEN YOU'RE HANGING OUT.
- YOU GUYS ARE, LIKE,
BEST FRIENDS, SERIOUSLY.
- ROGER AND I DEFINITELY
PULLED THIS OFF.
THE GIRLS WERE BEYOND IMPRESSED.
IT WAS A SUCCESSFUL NIGHT.
- BABE, I'M PROUD OF YOU.
- TWO, THREE HOURS AGO,
I WAS NOT EXPECTING
THIS NIGHT TO END LIKE THIS.
- I THINK WE DID GOOD, BRO.
I THINK WE DID GOOD.
- YOU GUYS DID AMAZING.
- COME HERE, BABE.
GET OVER HERE.
- THANK YOU.
- THANKS, BABE.
- YOU GUYS DO TOO MUCH FOR US.
- WE DO LOVE YOU.
- THIS DINNER IS DEFINITELY
LETTING US KNOW
THAT THEY DO LOVE US
AND THEY APPRECIATE US.
- SO PROUD OF THEM.
- YEAH.
- IT WAS PERFECT.
- I'M, LIKE, TURNED ON.
LIKE, ME AND JIONNI WANT TO GET
OUT OF HERE, SO WE CAN...
- GET OUT OF HERE, GIRL.
- DO IT UP.
- BYE, I LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU.
- BYE.
[laughter]
- SEE, WE GOT CUT OFF AGAIN.
- GET OFF HER, GET OFF HER.
- [laughing]
THANKS, ROGER.
- GET HOME SAFE.
- I HOPE YOU ENJOYED EVERYTHING.
- [laughs]
YOU GUYS ARE FUNNY.
- ALL RIGHT.
- THANK YOU FOR MAKING ME
FEEL LIKE A PRINCESS.
- I DON'T FEEL LIKE CLEANING
THIS PLACE UP TONIGHT.
I'M SO TIRED.
YOU WANT TO GO TO BED?
- YOU'RE THE BEST.
I'M VERY IMPRESSED.
- THANKS, BABE.
- WASN'T EXPECTING THAT.
- WHO'S YOUR DADDY, BUBBA?
OH! WHO'S YOUR DADDY, BUBBA?
[murmuring]
- THAT IS SO CUTE.
- BUBBA.
AFTER THIS DINNER,
I'M READY
TO SOUFFLE THE [bleep]
OUT OF JENNI.
- I JUST WANT TO LAY DOWN
FOR A MINUTE.
I'M TIRED.
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING.
- [snoring]
- I KIND OF WANT TO GO
ON VACATION.
- OH, GOD.
- I ALREADY BOOKED A TRIP.
- WHERE ARE WE GOING?
- A DUDE RANCH!
- A WHO?
- YOU GUYS EVER
MILKED A PIG BEFORE?
- MILKED A PIG?
- NO.
- CAN YOU MILK A PIG?
I NEVER HEARD OF THAT.
- [gasps]
- EW!
[blathering]
OH, MY GOD. I HATE THIS.
- HEADS UP!