- THE LAST TIME YOU SAW US,
WE WERE JUST YOUNG AND STUPID.
- [burps]
- DID YOU JUST FART?
- [laughs]
NOW WE'RE MATURE AND SEXY.
[imitates horse whinny]
[cheering]
- HE'S GONNA WALK.
- OH, MY GOD!
- AAH!
JIONNI AND I, WE'RE PRETTY USED
TO PARENTHOOD NOW.
[gasps]
- PFFT.
- CAN YOU REMIND ME THAT I NEED
TO GET MY BIRTH CONTROL?
- YES. I WILL DEFINITELY
REMIND YOU OF THAT.
- STOP!
- BABE, I LOVE YOU.
- YOU HAVE FIVE SECONDS
TO GET OUT OF MY ASS.
ME AND ROGER'S RELATIONSHIP
IS BASICALLY THE SAME [bleep],
DIFFERENT TOILET.
LET ME ENJOY MY MOMENT.
WE FIGHT...
[laughs]
YOU STUPID ASS!
WE DON'T HAVE SEX LIKE USUAL.
BUT WE'RE MAKING PROGRESS.
DIESEL, SAVE YOUR MOMMY!
- I'M SO EXCITED!
WE'RE GONNA GO OUT.
WE'RE GONNA ENJOY OURSELVES.
WE'RE GONNA DRINK.
WE'RE GONNA PARTY.
- [grunts]
- HOW DO YOU PEE IN THIS?
- WE'RE MAKING
NEW MEMORIES NOW.
IT'S LIKE A NEW CHAPTER.
- WHOO!
- [laughs]
- YOUR FAT ASS BROKE IT.
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
- CAN I HAVE SOME SUGAR?
I HAVE BUTTERFLIES.
- WHY?
- IT'S LIKE THE FIRST TIME.
CAN I JUST HAVE ONE KISS?
JIONNI, WHAT ARE YOU,
FIVE?
[laughs]
STOP.
- [humming]
SERIOUSLY?
IT'S DISGUSTING.
- MOM.
- OH, MY GOD. I'M SWEATING.
- YOU'LL END UP
PREGNANT AGAIN.
- I LOVE JANIS
AND EVERYONE.
- WE JUST NEED PRIVACY,
OKAY?
IT'S HARDER IN THE BASEMENT
TO BE ROMANTIC.
- YES.
- WE NEED OUR OWN HOUSE.
THANKS FOR DOING
OUR CLOTHES.
- YOU SAY THAT EVERY NIGHT.
- THANK YOU. BYE.
- LOOK, YOU'RE GETTING
SO BIG.
- YOU'RE GONNA BE ONE SOON.
- YOU REALLY ARE TAKING UP TOO
MUCH SPACE DOWN HERE.
- YOU TOOK OVER.
WE NEED A BIGGER PLACE.
THE BASEMENT IS A GOOD SIZE
IF YOU'RE SINGLE.
THAT USED TO BE
YOUR POOL TABLE.
THAT'S NOT
YOUR POOL TABLE ANYMORE.
HIS DIAPERS
ARE ON YOUR BAR.
WELL, WITH LORENZO
IN THE PICTURE,
IT'S JUST EVERYTHING
JUST GETS MORE CRAMPED,
AND THERE'S MORE TOYS,
AND, YOU KNOW,
WE JUST NEED MORE SPACE
FOR OUR SON.
HALF THE BASEMENT IS HIS.
- MAMA TOOK DADDY'S CLOSET.
- OH, MY GOD.
YOU SAID YOU WANTED TO GO
IN THE BOILER ROOM.
- THE BOILER ROOM
IS MY CLOSET.
- BUT YOU WANTED TO GO
IN THERE.
- NO, I DIDN'T WANT TO GO.
- I DIDN'T PUSH HIM IN THERE.
- I DIDN'T WANT TO GO
IN THE BOILER ROOM.
- YEAH, YOU SAID,
"I HAVE A GREAT IDEA.
WHY DON'T I GO
IN THE BOILER ROOM?"
- YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
"LET'S GO IN THE BOILER ROOM."
- AND I SAID, "YES!
MY OWN CLOSET."
- BUT WE REALLY NEED TO DO
SOMETHING.
- THAT'S WHY IT'S THE PERFECT
TIME TO MOVE OUT.
THIS SUMMER, I AM RENTING
MY OWN SHORE HOUSE FOR ME,
JIONNI, AND LORENZO.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE A TEST.
LIKE,
WE'RE GONNA PLAY HOUSE
TO SEE HOW WE ARE JUST,
LIKE, BY OURSELVES.
ARE YOU NERVOUS AT ALL
TO BE ON YOUR OWN?
- I'M NERVOUS 'CAUSE,
LIKE,
WE'RE NOT GONNA HAVE
ANYBODY UPSTAIRS.
- OH, HE'S SWEATY.
- THIS IS, LIKE,
LEGIT ON OUR OWN.
IF WE SCREW UP,
MY MOM IS UPSTAIRS.
IN THE HOUSE, SHE'S NOT.
- REMEMBER THAT ONE TIME
HE [bleep] ALL THE WAY
UP HIS NECK?
- YEAH.
- AND YOUR MOM HELPED US.
- PFFT.
- GUARANTEED,
WE MISS HER IN A WEEK.
- DEPEND ON NOBODY
BUT OURSELVES.
WHO'S GONNA TELL HER?
- UM, YOU,
BECAUSE YOU'RE HER SON.
- YOU KNOW, IF WE GO DOWN
TO THE SHORE,
OUR MOMS ARE GONNA
FREAK OUT, RIGHT?
- BUT WE'VE GOT TO
GET OUT OF HERE.
- OH, MY GOD.
WE'RE SCREWED.
- YEAH, WE'RE SCREWED.
both: WE'RE GOING DOWN
TO THE SHORE.
WE'RE GOING
DOWN TO THE SHORE.
- FIST BUMP.
- DON'T.
- YOU'RE GONNA GO TO KARMA
AND GO,
"BOM, BOM, BOM, BOM, BOM."
NEVER MIND.
- YOU ARE NOT GOING TO KARMA.
- NO FIST BUMP?
- THERE'S KOOKY GIRLS
AT KARMA.
- THAT'S WHERE DADDY
MET MOMMY.
- THERE'S KOOKY GIRLS
AT KARMA.
- [laughs]
HEY, JIONNI!
[laughs]
both: MMM.
- * TAKIN' BAD BOYS
HOME WITH ME *
* TAKE 'EM BACK... *
- HEY, BABE.
- HI.
- WHAT YOU DOING?
- SOMEONE POOPED
IN THE HALLWAY.
BELLA TOOK A [bleep]
ON THE RUG OUTSIDE,
AND DIESEL HELD IT
THE WHOLE TIME.
- HE'S THE BEST DOG.
YOU'VE GOTTA SAY, HE REALLY IS.
- [barks]
- REST MY CASE.
- THANKS.
SHE--I'LL NEVER UNDERSTAND
THAT ABOUT HER.
SHE FREAKS OUT.
- THAT'S WHY I'LL BE RAISING OUR
CHILDREN, IF WE EVER HAVE ANY.
- DIESEL IS MY CHILD.
- NO, I DON'T CONSIDER
THOSE TWO MY DOGS.
- WELL, WHY AREN'T MY CHILDREN
YOUR CHILDREN?
- THEY KIND OF ARE.
THEY'RE LIKE ILLEGITIMATE
STEPCHILDREN, LIKE.
- YOU ARE, LIKE,
0 FOR 10 RIGHT NOW.
- I'LL TAKE NOELLE.
IF THERE WAS A DIVORCE,
AND YOU PERISHED,
I WOULD TAKE NOELLE.
- IF I DIE IN A HORRIFIC
CAR ACCIDENT TOMORROW,
YOU WOULD NOT TAKE CARE
OF BELLA FOR ME?
- YOU WOULD SEE BELLA
IN A STOREFRONT WINDOW,
LOOKING FOR A HOME.
- WHY AM I DATING YOU?
THIS IS WHY I'M NOT
GETTING MARRIED.
- [laughs]
- [bleep]
- [clears throat]
WHERE IS YOUR RING,
BY THE WAY?
- OH, IT'S UPSTAIRS IN THE
BATHROOM, WHEN I WAS CLEANING.
- SO, YOU JUST DON'T
PUT IT BACK ON?
YOU JUST LEAVE IT HANGING?
BASICALLY, I GAVE UP
BOTH OF MY KIDNEYS
AND MY FIRSTBORN CHILD
FOR THIS RING,
AND I THINK JENNI
NEEDS TO WEAR IT MORE.
I LET CHICKS KNOW
IMMEDIATELY.
I'M, LIKE,
"I'M TAKEN, GIRL."
YOU'VE GOT NOTHING
THAT SAYS YOU'RE TAKEN.
- IF I WANTED TO GET MARRIED
TOMORROW TO YOU,
YOU KNOW YOU'D GET MARRIED.
WHAT?
- I THOUGHT WE WERE ON
THE SAME PAGE WITH THE WEDDING.
I THOUGHT
WE DISCUSSED THAT, AND...
- I DON'T KNOW. I THINK
WE BOTH HAVE COLD FEET.
BUT I'M JUST SAYING THOUGH,
LIKE, IF I DRAGGED YOU
TO THE ALTAR, I FEEL
LIKE YOU'D SAY YES.
- [laughs]
- US GIRLS LOVE TO
TEST OUR MEN,
AND I KNOW WE DON'T WANT TO
GET MARRIED TOMORROW,
BUT IF I ASK HIM, YOU KNOW,
"WOULD YOU
GET MARRIED TOMORROW,"
I WANT HIM TO SAY, "YES."
- YEAH, NO, I'M NOT READY
TO GET MARRIED THIS WEEKEND, NO.
- NO?
- YOU HAVE SAID,
UP UNTIL TEN MINUTES AGO,
"I DON'T WANT TO GET MARRIED."
SO, WHERE IS THIS--ALL THIS
COMING FROM?
I DON'T GET IT. YOU'RE
BLOWING ME AWAY RIGHT NOW.
- OH, MY GOD. LIKE, THIS IS WHAT
I DEAL WITH ON A DAILY BASIS.
WHAT ROGER IS DOING RIGHT NOW
WITH THE NEGATIVE BULL[bleep]
IS THE REASON
WHY WE NEED THERAPY.
- IF IT WASN'T FOR NEGATIVITY,
YOU WOULD HAVE NO "TIVITY."
- YOU GOOD?
- NO, YOU JUST PISS ME OFF.
- [laughs]
- TODAY, I'M MEETING JENNI
AT NOT JUST DESSERTS,
ONE OF THOSE
BAKE-A-CAKE PLACES.
I CAN MAKE BROWNIES GOOD,
BUT I DON'T KNOW HOW TO BAKE.
EVEN THOUGH I'M REALLY BAD
AT IT, YOU KNOW,
YOU'VE GOTTA LEARN.
IT'S FOR LORENZO'S SAKE.
- I MEAN, THIS SHOULD BE
NO PROBLEM, RIGHT?
IT CAN'T BE THAT HARD.
- NAH.
- IT'S JUST A CAKE.
- THE FIRST STEP
TO MAKING A CAKE IS,
I HAVE NO [bleep] IDEA.
- OH.
- LET'S JUST DECORATE
THE CAKE FIRST, I FEEL.
- IT SHOULDN'T BE THAT--
- GET THE OTHER LAYER.
- IT'S STUCK.
- STOP.
- IT AIN'T GOING ANYWHERE.
OKAY, NOW, IT'S GOING.
- OH.
JENNI.
- IT'S FINE.
IT'S A WORK IN PROGRESS.
- WHOA.
- ALL YOU'VE GOT TO DO IS ICE--
- AAH!
FIVE SECOND RULE.
- WE NEED A NEW BASE.
- NO, WE'LL FIX IT.
WE'LL JUST STICK IT TOGETHER.
THIS IS LIKE A LAVA CAKE.
- WE'LL JUST DECORATE IT.
- OKAY.
- DID YOU THINK ABOUT ANYTHING
FOR YOUR WEDDING YET?
- I DECIDED I WANT TO GET
MARRIED BY NEXT YEAR.
- OH, REALLY?
- YEAH.
- I LOVE THAT.
- USUALLY, IT TAKES A YEAR,
SO, LIKE,
I'VE GOT TO START NOW,
SO I NEED TO START
LOOKING AT VENUES,
TRY ON DRESSES.
- WE DIDN'T START PLANNING.
WE'RE NOT GONNA PLAN.
WHAT HAPPENS IF ROGER
GOES BALD IN 20 YEARS?
LIKE, DO I HAVE TO
DEAL WITH THAT?
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU
MARRY THAT PERSON,
YOU'RE WITH THEM FOR LIFE.
- YOU THINK TOO MUCH.
JUST GO WITH THE FLOW.
- YEAH, WELL, I WANT TO GO
SEE A THERAPIST WITH ROGER.
- WHY DO YOU HAVE TO GO
TO A THERAPIST?
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH THAT?
- ARE YOU HAVING PROBLEMS?
- I WANT TO DO
COUPLES THERAPY
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE
ME AND ROGER
NEED SOMEONE
TO KIND OF MODERATE
AND TELL US WHAT TO DO,
UNLESS THE THERAPIST
SAYS THAT HE'S RIGHT.
THEN, I'LL CUT
THE THERAPIST'S [bleep] OFF.
- I COULD BE YOUR THERAPIST.
DO YOU GUYS HAVE SEX?
- LIKE, ONCE A WEEK MAYBE.
- UH, WE HAVE SEX,
LIKE, ONCE A MONTH.
- IS IT 'CAUSE OF LORENZO?
- WELL, EVERY TIME I TRY
AND HAVE SEX WITH HIM,
HE FALLS ASLEEP.
- OH, YEAH.
- I THINK IT'S JUST
NEW PARENT SYNDROME.
- YOU'VE HEARD
HOW I'VE HAD SEX.
THAT [bleep] EXHAUSTING.
- IT SOUNDS SO PAINFUL.
I CAN'T.
BIG DINOSAUR [bleep].
- [laughs]
I CAN NEVER BE WITH
ANOTHER MAN AFTER HIM.
- SERIOUSLY.
HEY, I CAN'T TALK.
I HAD A BABY, BUT I DID
GET THE EXTRA STITCH.
TA-DA!
WE DID A GREAT JOB.
- I FEEL LIKE
WE SCREWED UP.
- MAYBE IF WE HAD
INSTRUCTIONS.
- THE EGYPTIANS
DIDN'T HAVE INSTRUCTIONS
WHEN THEY BUILT THE PYRAMIDS,
BUT THEY--
- YES, THEY [bleep] DID.
- WHO INSTRUCTED THEM?
- THE CATS.
- OH, THE CATS. I'M SORRY.
ALL RIGHT.
- LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
- YEAH, LET'S LEAVE.
- ME AND JENNI
ARE BASICALLY
SNEAKING OUT OF THIS BAKERY
RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE DIDN'T REALLY DO
A GOOD JOB.
- WHAT THE--
- [screams]
- OH!
[laughs]
- I'M BLIND!
- IT WASN'T
SUPPOSED TO BREAK!
- JENNI,
I CAN'T OPEN MY EYES.
WHAT THE [bleep]
IS WRONG WITH YOU?
- I JUST WANTED TO
GET YOU A LITTLE BIT
WITH THE WATER BOTTLE.
- I CAN'T [bleep] SEE!
BRING ME TO ORTHOPEDICS.
- * REINVENT YOURSELF *
- LET'S GO, GIRLS.
- UHH!
- TODAY, WE ARE GOING TO
HAVE A LITTLE GIRLS' DAY.
[dog barks]
OH!
- STOP THE FIGHTING!
[bleep]!
- LORENZO
IS SO MUCH EASIER.
I'M REALLY EXCITED TO GO
TO THE NAIL SALON
BECAUSE I HAVEN'T
GOT A "PEDICORE"
IN GOD KNOWS HOW LONG.
- "PEDICORE"?
[both laugh]
I TOTALLY HEARD IT.
- I SAID "PEDICORE"?
- I'M JUST GETTING
MY NAILS PAINTED.
- IS IT WEIRD THAT
I'M EXCITED FOR THAT?
- NO, THAT'S
DEFINITELY CUTE.
[dog barks]
- WHOA!
UHH!
- STOP IT! SIT! RELAX!
I DON'T WANT TO LEAVE 'EM COOPED
UP IN THE HOUSE ALL DAY.
- BUT YOU CAN.
OOH.
- STOP IT.
- ARE YOU GROWLING AT ME?
- WOULD YOU LEAVE LORENZO COOPED
UP IN THE HOUSE ALL DAY?
- LORENZO IS A CHILD.
- SO ARE MY BABIES.
[dog growls]
- OOH.
STOP IT.
- STOP IT, NOELLE.
- I'M NOT SAYING
I DON'T LOVE 'EM,
BUT WE COULD HAVE
LEFT 'EM HOME.
DO YOU TAKE THEM
EVERYWHERE LIKE THAT?
- I MEAN,
I WOULD LIKE TO--
- LIKE, HOW DO YOU
ACCOMPLISH YOUR DAY?
- THEY'RE NOT BAD DOGS.
- THEY JUST NEED
A LITTLE, LIKE--
- DISCIPLINE?
- YEAH.
OH!
[dogs barking]
GIRLS.
GIRLS, KNOCK IT OFF.
- STOP IT.
- CUT IT OUT.
- I JUST WANT
MY NAILS DONE.
THAT'S ALL I WANT.
- WE'RE GOING
IN A NAIL SALON, OKAY?
OH, GOD.
I JUST STEPPED ON ITS PAW.
- OH, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
IT'S NO PET ALLOWED.
- HUH?
- NO PET ALLOWED.
- REALLY? NO PETS?
- YEP.
- BUT THEY'RE LIKE BABIES.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
- OH.
- OH, GOD.
SHE TINKLED ON YOUR CARPET
ALREADY.
- "SHE PEED. SHE PEED.
SHE PEED."
I'M, LIKE, "SHUT UP."
"SHE PEED."
YOU COMPLETELY THREW ME
UNDER THE BUS.
YOU'RE AN [bleep], DUDE.
LET'S GO SHOPPING.
[dogs barking]
- AAH! STOP IT!
GIRLS, GIRLS,
KNOCK IT OFF.
- HI.
- OH.
- HELLO.
- OH, MY GOD, WHAT IS THIS?
YOU DID NOT.
- YEAH.
OH, BELLA, BELLA.
- OH, LORDY LOU.
ARE THEY GONNA [bleep]
ON MY RUG?
both: PROBABLY.
- GREAT.
- I UNDERSTAND
PEOPLE'S CONCERNS,
BUT ME BEING ME,
I DON'T CARE.
- WE JUST LIVE IN
JENNI'S WORLD.
EVERYONE LIVES
IN JENNI'S WORLD.
- THANK YOU.
I'M LOCKING THE DOOR.
- YOU BETTER BEHAVE YOURSELF,
MISTER.
- ARE YOU TRYING TO HUMP ME
RIGHT NOW?
YOU'RE REALLY TRYING
TO HUMP ME RIGHT NOW?
- WHOA.
- STOP IT. STOP IT.
- OH, LORD.
I THINK HE WAS SODOMIZING HER.
- DIESEL.
- IS THAT PEE?
- ARE THESE MINE
OR YOURS?
- IS THAT PEE ON MY FLOOR?
- I'LL PAY
FOR STANLEY STEAMER.
- THIS LADY IS NEVER GONNA
LET US INTO HER STORE ANYMORE,
AND THAT SUCKS BECAUSE SHE HAS
REALLY NICE STUFF,
SO THANKS, DOGS.
I DON'T LIKE SHOPPING
WITH THEM.
[dogs barking]
- AAH! STOP IT!
- [barks]
- STOP.
[dogs barking]
- HELLO, HELLO.
- HELLO.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD. HOW ARE YOU?
- MAY WE SIT AND POSSIBLY GET
FOOD AND DRINK?
- YEAH.
- UH, I CAN DO
THE DRINKS AND STUFF,
AND THEN I HAVE TO ASK YOU TO
SIT OUTSIDE WITH THEM.
CAN'T HAVE DOGS IN.
- THAT'S NICE.
- DISCRIMINATION.
I FEEL, LIKE, SEGREGATED.
- WHERE ARE YOU LEARNING
THESE WORDS?
- I'M TELLING YOU, LIKE,
MY BRAIN IS JUST EXPANDING.
WHEN I GET OLDER, I JUST FEEL
MORE WISER AND SMARTER.
- ARE YOU BLIND?
- WHY'D YOU ASK IF I WAS BLIND?
- BLIND PEOPLE NEED DOGS.
MAYBE IF THEY WERE
SERVICE DOGS,
WE'D LET YOU HANG OUT
TILL WE CLOSE, BUT...
- I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHY
I DIDN'T THINK OF THIS BEFORE.
I'LL GET MY DOG SERVICED
EVEN THOUGH I'M NOT BLIND,
BUT I'LL SAY I'M BLIND.
I WANT TO GET YOU SERVICED.
ALL I NEED IS SOME
REALLY DARK, HUGE SUNGLASSES,
A WHITE STICK,
AND JUST BUMP INTO THINGS--
WHICH I BUMP INTO THINGS
HALF THE TIME ANYWAYS.
I'M EXCITED FOR YOU
TO PLAN YOUR WEDDING.
- [gasps]
ME TOO.
- I'M EXCITED FOR YOU
TO TRY ON WEDDING DRESSES,
AND I'LL TRY ONE ON.
- OKAY.
- HEY, MAYBE I'LL GET THE ITCH
WHEN I START PLANNING WITH YOU.
- YOU WILL.
ONCE YOU SEE ME IN THAT DRESS
WALKING DOWN,
YOU'LL BE, LIKE,
"I WANT MY DAY NOW."
- AND I WANT TO SEE
HOW HOT I WOULD LOOK
IF I DECIDE TO GET MARRIED,
'CAUSE I'M VAIN.
- WHAT IS VAIN?
- SERIOUSLY?
- YES.
- VAIN. YOU'RE VAIN.
YOU ARE THE EPITOME OF VAIN.
- OKAY.
VAIN MEANS CONCEITED,
RIGHT?
THAT'S YOU TOO, BITCH.
PLEASE.
ARE YOU READY TO GET GOING?
- YEAH, IF YOU ARE.
- I'M EXHAUSTED,
JUST WATCHING THESE KIDS.
THIS IS NOT HOW I
IMAGINED THE DAY TO BE.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
THAT THE DOGS WERE COMING.
LIKE, SICK GIRLS' DAY.
[dogs barking]
- WHOA!
- OH, MY GOD.
I'M DRUGGING YOU ALL.
- * SEEKING OUT PASSION... *
[dogs barking]
- WHEN IT COMES TO MARRIAGE,
LIKE, I'M VERY APPREHENSIVE,
AND CLEARLY, ME AND ROGER ARE
NOT THE BEST AT COMPROMISING
AND GETTING THROUGH THINGS,
SO RIGHT NOW
I JUST WANT TO GET MY
RELATIONSHIP BACK ON TRACK.
- HI.
RICH PORESKY.
- HI, I AM INTERESTED
IN COUPLES COUNSELING.
I WAS WONDERING IF YOU'RE
AVAILABLE SOON?
- HOW WOULD TOMORROW BE,
AROUND 5:00?
- THAT'S PERFECT, ACTUALLY.
I CAN'T WAIT TO MEET YOU.
- BYE-BYE.
- DIESEL, MOMMY
FOUND A THERAPIST.
SOUNDS NICE.
THINK HE CAN FIX YOU?
GOOD TALK, DIESEL.
NOW, THE HARD PART
IS TO TELL ROGER
THAT I ALREADY MADE AN
APPOINTMENT WITH A THERAPIST.
ARE YOU DONE? NO?
ARE YOU DONE?
ROGER DOESN'T HAVE
FAITH IN ANYTHING.
LET'S GO
TO THE LIVING ROOM.
- LIVING ROOM?
WHAT IS THIS?
IMPORTANT TALKS
OR SOMETHING?
- SO, I'M VERY AFRAID THAT
WHEN I BRING UP THE THERAPIST,
ROGER IS GONNA SAY, "NOBODY
CAN FIX US BUT OURSELVES.
BUH, BUH, BUH. THAT'S NOT...
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH."
AND IT'S JUST GONNA BE A HUGE
HEADACHE AND A FIGHT,
AND I AM NOT
LOOKING FORWARD TO IT.
[sighs]
I CALLED A FEW THERAPISTS
AND I MADE AN APPOINTMENT
FOR TOMORROW.
- THERAPISTS AS FAR AS--
- COUPLES COUNSELING.
- [sighs]
YOU MEAN THE THING PEOPLE DO
RIGHT BEFORE THEY GET A DIVORCE?
- * SHE HAS BEEN WAITING
FOR FAR TOO LONG *
- I CALLED A FEW THERAPISTS
AND I MADE AN APPOINTMENT
FOR TOMORROW.
- YOU MEAN THE THING PEOPLE DO
RIGHT BEFORE THEY GET A DIVORCE?
- MAYBE THEY
SAVE THE MARRIAGE.
- ARE WE THAT BAD?
- I DON'T FIND THAT YOU--
I THINK YOU HAVE,
LIKE, A STIGMA AGAINST IT.
- IT TAKES A LONG TIME
TO GET TO KNOW SOMEBODY,
SO WHAT, DO WE GO FOR,
YOU KNOW, $10,000 WORTH,
AND THEN THEY GET TO KNOW US
ENOUGH TO MAKE AN ASSESSMENT?
YOU KNOW,
THAT'S RIDICULOUS TO ME.
IT'S A GLORIFIED,
OVERPAID MODERATOR.
"DESCRIBE YOUR LIFE TO ME
AND, YOU KNOW,
BUTTERFLIES AND RAINBOWS."
I'M NEVER GONNA BE THE GUY
THAT GOES TO THERAPY
AND HAS A BREAKDOWN
AND CRIES IN THE CORNER,
LIKE, "I MISS MY MOMMY."
IT'S NEVER GONNA HAPPEN.
- HE MISSES HIS MOM.
- YEAH.
- WELL, ARE YOU TELLING ME
THAT WE'RE GOING
OR ARE YOU ASKING ME
MY TAKE ON IT?
- WELL, I ALREADY MADE
THE APPOINTMENT.
- OH, SO I DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
I'M JUST GOING?
- MM-HMM.
- AM I EXCITED ABOUT IT?
NO.
- [sighs]
- DO YOU THINK THIS GUY
CAN HELP US?
IT CAN'T HURT RIGHT?
THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE GONNA SAY.
ALL RIGHT, BABE, IF YOU
WANT TO GO, I'LL GO.
- THANK YOU.
- POW!
- AAH!
JESUS.
[both laugh]
I HAVE A BOOGER.
- AWESOME. MAYBE YOU
SHOULD TELL HIM THAT.
- YOU ARE JUST
POSITIVE PETE OVER THERE.
- [laughs]
- * NEVER STOP FOR NO ONE *
* THAT'S THE WAY
I'M GROWING *
* JUST KEEP IT COMING *
- OW! I'M SORE.
BUT DON'T STOP THOUGH.
CAN I JUST HAVE ONE KISS?
- OH, GOD.
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'RE READY TO
HAVE SEX OR SOMETHING.
- [laughs]
EW!
YOUR MOM SAID "SEX."
- SEX.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- RUBBING HER LEGS, OBVIOUSLY.
- OH, GOD.
- YOU WEIRDO.
- BYE.
I LOVE YOUR MOM,
BUT THIS IS WHY
WE NEED TO GET OUT OF HERE.
- [sighs]
YEAH, I'M KIND OF AFRAID
TO TELL MY MOM
THAT WE'RE LEAVING HER.
SHE'S GONNA BE SAD.
- SHE'S GONNA FREAK OUT.
SO, YOU SAY,
"HEY, MOM, LISTEN.
WE'VE GOT TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING."
THEN, AUTOMATICALLY,
SHE'LL THINK I'M PREGNANT.
- SHE'S GONNA ASK TO COME.
- SHE CAN'T, LIKE,
MOVE IN WITH US
'CAUSE THAT'S WHY
WE'RE MOVING OUT.
- SO YOU'RE
TELLING HER FIRST?
- NO.
- I'M NOT TELLING HER.
- JIONNI, PLEASE TELL HER.
I'M NOT KIDDING.
- YOU'RE TELLING HER,
NOT ME.
- I'M NOT TELLING HER.
SHE'S YOUR MOTHER.
- YOU'RE GONNA TELL HER.
- YOU'RE NERVOUS.
ARE YOU'RE PRAYING?
- MY MOM DOESN'T YELL.
- SHE'S GONNA BE VERY SAD.
- YOU TELL HER.
- NO!
- HI.
- SHH.
- YOU TELL HER.
YOU TELL HER. YOU TELL HER.
YOU HAVE TO TELL HER.
YOU TELL HER.
YOU TELL HER. YOU TELL HER.
- HEY, GUYS.
both: HEY.
- I'M RUNNING TO THE STORE.
YOU GUYS NEED ANYTHING?
DIAPERS, FORMULA?
- NO.
- WHAT?
- JIONNI HAS SOMETHING
TO TELL YOU.
JIONNI.
- WHY ARE YOU SO SERIOUS?
- JIONNI,
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
- WE'RE GONNA GO DOWN
TO THE SHORE FOR THE SUMMER.
- IS THIS A JOKE?
- THERE'S MORE SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW
ON THE WAY...
- AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
- WE HAVE SOMETHING
TO TELL YOU.
WE'RE GONNA GO DOWN TO
THE SHORE FOR THE SUMMER.
- IS THIS A JOKE?
YOU'RE GOING DOWN TO THE SHORE
FOR THE WHOLE SUMMER?
- WE GOT A HOUSE.
LIKE, A NICE HOUSE.
- FOR THE WHOLE SUMMER?
- YEAH.
- I'LL PUT IN FOR
A VACATION TOMORROW.
- [bleep].
- OH, MY GOD.
I LOVE YOU, BUT BACK AWAY.
- I COULD COME DOWN,
RIGHT?
- TO VISIT, NICOLE SAID.
- YEAH.
- YOU SAID "VISIT"?
- I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
- SHE DID?
- HE--NO.
YOU COULD COME
WHENEVER YOU WANT.
- I'VE GOT TO CUT THE CORD
SOMEHOW, MA.
- THIS ISN'T CUTTING
THE CORD.
I'M COMING OVER EVERY DAY.
I'M ACTUALLY THINKING
OF MOVING IN.
- OH, [bleep]
- IT'S LIKE,
YOU CAN COME VISIT,
BUT THIS IS OUR PLACE.
- THE KEY WORD
IN THERE--VISIT.
- MM-HMM.
- YOU CAN COME VISIT.
- YOU'RE LEAVING ME
FOR THE WHOLE SUMMER?
- UH-HUH.
IT'S REALLY NICE.
IT'S ON THE BAY.
LORENZO HAS HIS OWN ROOM.
WE CAN HAVE SUNDAY DINNERS.
- LORENZO IS GOING TOO?
- JANIS IS NOT HAPPY
THAT WE'RE LEAVING.
- NO WAY.
KITCHEN WITH MY DAD
THE WHOLE TIME?
- YEAH!
- STARTING AT EACH OTHER.
- OH, NO.
- THAT'S AWKWARD.
- YEAH. I FEEL BAD, BUT...
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
- YOU'VE GOTTA PACK.
YOU KNOW WHAT TO PACK?
- YEAH, WE HAVE A LOT
OF PACKING TO DO.
- YEAH, WE'RE GONNA START
PACKING.
- THE WHOLE SUMMER?
FOR REAL?
- YEAH.
- OH, MY LORD.
- LOVE YOU.
- OH, MY GOD.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
YEAH, LORENZO IS
STAYING WITH ME.
- NO.
- LET'S GET DONE PACKING.
- THAT WENT GOOD.
- GOOD JOB.
- I GOT BOXES FOR US
AND BUBBLE WRAP.
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
WITH BUBBLE WRAP?
- POP THE BUBBLES.
- [laughs]
- I FEEL LIKE THIS SUMMER
AS A FAMILY,
WE'RE GONNA BE GREAT.
WE'RE GONNA GROW MORE
AS PARENTS AND AS A COUPLE.
THIS COULD BE, LIKE,
A HOUSE.
WE SHOULD MAKE A LITTLE FORT
FOR LORENZO.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
A MILLION MEMORIES.
THIS IS JUST THE START
TO OUR FAMILY TRADITION,
SO I HAVE, YOU KNOW,
HIGH HOPES FOR THE SUMMER.
WE COULD CUT OUT, LIKE,
A LITTLE WINDOW,
AND IT COULD BE, LIKE,
LORENZO'S LITTLE HOUSE.
- ALL RIGHT. LET ME SEE.
- NO.
- JUST GO IN.
- THERE'S A GHOST IN HERE.
20 BUCKS
IF YOU CAN PICK ME UP.
- OKAY. HOLD ON.
- 20 BUCKS
IF YOU CAN PICK ME UP.
[screams]
- I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
- JIONNI?
JIONNI!
[grunts]
THIS IS SO RUDE.
JIONNI!
BABE!
- THIS IS THE MOMENT WE'VE BEEN
WAITING FOR FOREVER.
- OH, MY GOD.
- WELCOME HOME.
I LOST MY BOOBS.
- GET SOME BOLT-ONS LIKE JENNI.
OFF TO THERAPY WE GO.
I KNOW THAT I NEED TO
WORK ON ROMANCE.
HONEY, WAKE UP, WAKE UP!
- THIS IS NOT ROMANCE.
THIS IS MOLESTATION.
- BUT I WOULD LIKE TO PULL
JENNI'S SKIRT DOWN
AND RAVAGE HER.
- SO, SHE'S A SEXY LADY?
- UGH!
- IT'S NICE TO BE BACK
AT THE SHORE.
- IT'S, LIKE,
THE NEW BOOK.
IT'S NOT EVEN A NEW CHAPTER.
IT'S A NEW BOOK.
- YEAH.
- ALL RIGHT,
LET'S ALL DIVE IN.
- WHOA!
- AAH!
- DON'T, DON'T!
STOP, STOP, STOP, PLEASE!