- BABE, HE WANTS ME.
- NO, HE WANTS ME.
- [kissing]
- WHY DOESN'T HE LIKE ME?
- ♪ BUM BUM BUM BUM ♪
- WE'RE JUST SIMPLY GOING
TO ASK QUESTIONS...RIGHT?
WE'RE OFF
TO AN ADOPTION FAIR.
- IT DOES SOUND WEIRD--
ADOPTION FAIR.
- I'LL RACE YOU, ROGER.
- YOU WANNA RACE?
I'LL RACE YOU.
WHERE WE RACING TO?
- SEEING THESE PARENTS
AND THEIR CHILDREN
MAKES ME REALIZE
THAT ME AND ROGER
COULD BE THESE PEOPLE
ONE DAY.
- ♪ I DON'T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT ♪
♪ I DON'T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT ♪
♪ I DON'T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I DON'T CARE ♪
- WHAT IF THAT PLACE
I WANT TO ADOPT
DOESN'T ACCEPT
NON-MARRIED COUPLES?
- YOU'RE GETTING
WAY TOO FAR AHEAD OF YOURSELF.
YOU'RE MOVING
AT WARP SPEED 9.
WE HAVE SO MANY THINGS
GOING ON RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE IN THERAPY, WE'RE LOOKING
INTO ADOPTION CENTERS,
AND, LIKE...
THAT'S A LOT.
THAT'S MOVING TOO FAST
IN MY BOOK, YOU KNOW?
- SORRY I BROUGHT IT UP.
- DON'T BE SORRY.
EXPRESS HOW YOU FEEL.
BUT YOU'LL ALL OVER
YOUR PLACE WITH HOW YOU FEEL.
THAT'S WHAT'S CONFUSING ME.
I HONESTLY BELIEVE
THAT RIGHT NOW
WE ARE NOT
IN THE BEST POSITION...
- BUT IF I GOT PREGNANT NOW,
WE HAVE NINE MONTHS.
- TO DO THAT.
THAT'S NOW HOW I LOOK AT IT,
THOUGH.
I DON'T LOOK AT IT THAT WAY.
- IF WE DO IT YOUR WAY,
WE'RE GONNA BE 90!
- I'M ALREADY 90.
- YEAH, EXACTLY.
I WOULD LOVE TO SEE HOW YOU ARE
AROUND KIDS, THOUGH.
- YOU'VE SEEN ME AROUND KIDS.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- NO, BABY BABIES.
SO WE CAN KIND OF, LIKE,
GIVE YOU THE RUNDOWN
OF WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO TAKE CARE OF A BABY.
- THINK IT'S GONNA GO
A LITTLE SOMETHING LIKE THIS:
YOU MOVE
INTO YOUR PARENTS' BASEMENT.
YOU HAVE THEM HELP YOU A LOT.
- OH, MY GOD.
- I HAVEN'T SPENT
A LOT OF TIME WITH A BABY.
BABIES DEFINITELY
MAKE ME UNCOMFORTABLE.
I'M A BIG OGRE.
HOLDING SOMETHING
THAT LITTLE AND DELICATE--
IT'S A SCARY PREMISE.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT I WANT,
TO BE HONEST.
- HOW CAN I EVER MAKE YOU HAPPY
IF YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU WANT?
- YOU MAKE ME HAPPY
ON A DAY-TO-DAY BASIS.
YOU DO JUST FINE.
- THAT'S RIGHT, BUBBA.
- YOU WOULD HANG OUT
WITH LORENZO, WOULDN'T YOU?
- OF COURSE.
- OR TAKE CARE OF HIM?
- I LOVE HANGING OUT
WITH LORENZO
WHEN NICOLE AND JIONNI
ARE AROUND.
- MMM...SAUSAGE.
- FIRST TIME
I'VE EVER HEARD YOU SAY THAT.
[Jenni tapping nails]
[laughing]
SERIOUSLY.
[phone chiming]
- HELLO?
- HEY, BOO.
- HEY, WHAT'S UP?
- I JUST WANNA LET YOU KNOW
THAT ME AND ROGER
WENT TO AN ADOPTION PICNIC,
AND IT WAS REALLY AMAZING
AND INFORMATIVE.
THE ONLY THING THAT SUCKED
IS THAT THEY DIDN'T HAVE
BABIES THERE.
SO BECAUSE OF THAT,
I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU AND JIONNI AND ME
GIVE HIM, LIKE, A BABY BOOT CAMP
ON, LIKE, CHANGING DIAPERS,
FEEDING, HOLDING,
AND JUST, YOU KNOW,
REALLY GETTING COMFORTABLE.
- I'M TOTALLY DOWN FOR THAT.
WHY DON'T YOU AND ROGER
SLEEP OVER?
ME AND JIONNI WILL COOK DINNER,
AND THEN YOU CAN TAKE CARE
OF LORENZO ALL NIGHT.
- IT'S GONNA TAKE
MORE THAN ONE NIGHT
TO SEE WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO BE A PARENT.
TO BE HONEST,
ONLY BEING A PARENT
IS GONNA ALLOW YOU
TO BE A PARENT.
BUT HE'LL GET AN IDEA.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
- OKAY, BYE.
- BYE.
- [singsong]
LOOK WHAT MOMMY'S GOT!
- WHAT'S THAT?
- A PUPPET SHOW!
- OH, MY GOD.
LET'S GIVE LORENZO
A LITTLE SHOW.
TIME TO HAVE SOME FUN.
- HELLO, BOYS AND GIRLS.
TODAY WE ARE GOING TO BE
DOING A PUPPET SHOW.
ENJOY!
- [falsetto]
'SCUSE ME, LITTLE BOY.
HELLO, MR. SHEEP.
OH, I'M TALKING NOW, BUDDY.
- HEE-HAW!
- YOU'RE A HORSE,
NOT A DONKEY.
- [laughing]
- WHAT THE [bleep] ARE YOU--
I MEAN, NICOLE'S ANIMAL NOISES
ARE JUST WAY OFF.
BUT SHE HAS GOOD, UH...
IMPERSONATIONS.
- MM-HMM.
- [falsetto]
HELLO, MR. ELEPHANT.
- HELLO, PIG.
- WHAT KIND OF NOISES
DO YOU MAKE?
- MAAH!
- [laughing]
AN ELEPHANT DOESN'T DO THAT!
ARE YOU KIDDING?
I'M SORRY, SIR.
WE GOTTA START OVER.
IF LORENZO COULD TALK,
HE'D SAY, "WHAT THE--
WHAT IS GOING ON RIGHT NOW?"
- HE'S NOT GONNA TALK LIKE THAT.
YOU GO FIRST.
I'M TRYING TO THINK.
- THE CROWD'S GETTING ANTSY.
- CAN YOU PLEASE GO FIRST?
I'M TRYING TO THINK
WHAT ELEPHANTS DO--PLEASE?
- JUST GO--
- MAAAH!
[both laughing]
- THIS IS GETTING WEIRD.
SHOW'S OVER.
- [baby talking]
DID YOU ENJOY OUR LITTLE SHOW?
- WELL, IF ALL ELSE FAILS,
WE COULD BE MUPPETS.
- ♪ THERE GOES MY BABY,
TENDERLY SO ♪
- UNCLE ROGER'S COMING.
- LORENZO, IF YOU HAVE
TO GO POOPIES,
YOU WAIT, OKAY?
REMEMBER WE TALKED ABOUT
BEING GOOD FOR THE BABYSITTER?
WELL, DO THE OPPOSITE
FOR ROGER, OKAY?
- [shouts]
- I WOULD LOVE FOR ROGER
TO GET PEED ON
AND POOPED ON,
BECAUSE THAT'S ONLY
A LITTLE EXPERIENCE
OF WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO BE A PARENT.
I MEAN, THAT'S LIKE
EVERYDAY STUFF.
SOMETIMES I FIND POOP
UNDER MY NAILS.
- YOU DO?
- YEAH.
[knock at door]
- HELLO?
- GO SEE UNCLE ROGER,
COME ON.
- BIG PAPA'S HERE.
HI, BUDDY!
OH, MY GOD, YOU'RE GONNA
HAND HIM RIGHT OVER LIKE THAT?
- IT STARTS NOW.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
IT'S A LITTLE DAUNTING.
I JUST GOT THROUGH THE DOOR.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I HAVE TO DO.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
BABY BOOT CAMP CONSISTS OF.
LIKE, YOU KNOW, DO YOU SLOW UP
A LITTLE BIT, PUMP THE BRAKES?
SWITCH LANES?
MERGE?
- ALL RIGHT, ME AND JIONNI
ARE GONNA GO RELAX.
- BYE.
- HA HA. ARE YOU REALLY?
- WHERE YOU GOING?
- WE'RE JUST KIDDING.
- OH.
- THIS IS TRIAL BY FIRE.
- ME AND UNCLE ROGER ARE GOING
TO GET YOU SOMETHING TODAY.
- WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
[Lorenzo laughs]
- SWING SET!
- OH, YOU GUYS
ARE GOING TO DO THAT TODAY?
- A SWING SET?
WE'RE GONNA GO GET YOU
A SWING SET?
I KNOW JIONNI'S SKILL SET
WHEN IT COMES
TO PUTTING THINGS TOGETHER,
SO I'M SURE THIS IS GONNA BE
PROBABLY MORE A TASK FOR ME.
LET'S GO PLAY WITH TOYS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, HUH?
PFFT!
- [laughs]
- [gasps] PIGGIES!
LET ME GET THAT PIGGY TOE!
I WANNA GET
THAT LITTLE PIGGY TOE!
- OH, MY GOD.
ROGER IS--
- WHAT IS THAT VOICE?
- OH, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO HIT ME.
- WHUP HIS ASS, LORENZO.
- THAT'S A TIGHT FIT
FOR UNCLE ROG.
- SO I HAVE A LIST FOR YOU
SINCE THIS IS BABY BOOT CAMP.
- WHAT'S MY LIST?
- IF HE HAS A POOPY DIAPER,
YOU GOTTA CHANGE
THE POOPY DIAPER.
- I AM? OKAY.
- AND YOU'RE GONNA HELP ME
GIVE HIM A BATH.
- OKAY.
- AND THEN WE'RE GONNA
PUT HIM IN JAMMIES.
- I'M READY. I'M READY.
- NICOLE, WHEN I LEAVE,
STIR THAT EVERY
ABOUT 15 MINUTES.
LET'S GO GET THIS SWING SET.
- BRING ME BACK
ICE CREAM AND LOVE.
GOOD-BYE, UNCLE ROG.
- BYE!
- ROGER AND I ARE HEADING
OUT THE DOOR.
I'M GONNA GET A SWING SET
FOR LORENZO.
WHAT BETTER THAN THIS BIG,
STRONG GUY TO HELP ME CARRY IT?
- YEAH. HE'S PROBABLY GONNA
NEED A LITTLE HELP
WITH THE SWING SET,
YOU KNOW?
- I'M NOT BOB--
I'M NOT [bleep] MACGYVER.
- YOU'RE NOT BOB?
IS THAT MACGYVER'S FIRST NAME?
- I'M NOT MACGYVER.
- HE'S NOT BOB MACGYVER.
- I'M NOT MACGYVER. HI.
- HELLO.
- I'M LOOKING FOR SOME, UH...
PLAY SETS.
- OKAY.
WE GOT THEM IN THE BACK.
- SET MY LITTLE BUDDY UP
WITH SOMETHING NICE.
- DID YOU GUYS
HAVE ANYTHING IN MIND
WHAT YOU WERE LOOKING FOR?
- NO. I'M KINDA JUST LOOKING.
- HE'S A FRAGILE KID,
SO I DON'T WANT SOMETHING
TOO HIGH, YOU KNOW...
- CAN MY FATHER TEST
SOME OF THE THINGS OUT?
- I SMELL [bleep].
DID HE POOP?
- POOP!
- ROGER!
- COME ON, LITTLE BUDDY,
LET'S GET IN THERE.
- [laughs]
- [grunts]
I CAN'T GET UP.
PUSH.
[grunts, laughs]
I'M STUCK.
DUDE, SERIOUSLY.
LADIES,
CAN WE GET SOME HELP?
- YEAH, I'M COMING.
- I COULDN'T MOVE.
I COULDN'T GET OFF HIM.
AND HE COULDN'T GET OUT,
AND I KNOW HE WAS IN PAIN.
- [laughing] I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT TO DO RIGHT NOW.
- ALL RIGHT.
- [giggling]
[laughing]
- I THOUGHT MY LIFE WAS OVER.
I'M NOT EVEN KIDDING.
I LIKE THIS ONE.
- COME OVER HERE.
COME HERE.
LOVE YOU, LITTLE BUDDY.
I DO.
ALL RIGHT, LADIES,
I THINK WE'LL TAKE IT.
- OKAY.
- HE'S THE BEST FATHER
AROUND.
I WOULDN'T BE THE MAN I AM NOW
WITHOUT HIM.
- YOU WOULDN'T BE HALF THE MAN
YOU ARE NOW WITHOUT ME.
- HALF.
KEY WORD.
[rock music]
- BYE, THANK YOU.
- HOLD ON, LITTLE BUDDY.
- YOU'RE THE BEST, DAD.
- ♪ KIND OF MAN ♪
- I'M GONNA GET A DNA TEST.
- HOW OLD WERE YOU
WHEN YOU KNEW YOU WERE ADOPTED?
- WELL, THEY ADOPTED ME
AT SIX MONTHS,
BUT I FEEL LIKE
I ALWAYS KNEW.
- ARE YOU COMFORTABLE
TALKING ABOUT IT?
- YEAH.
- WAS IT HARD AS A KID?
- NO. I WAS JUST LIKE,
"OH, I'M ADOPTED,
BUT YOU'RE MY PARENTS."
BUT IT WOULD BE COOL TO KNOW
IF I WAS, LIKE, 100% CHILEAN.
I FEEL LIKE
SINCE I'M FROM CHILE...
I FEEL LIKE I AM CHILEAN,
BUT, I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW.
SO I WOULD LIKE TO KNOW.
OBVIOUSLY,
I KNOW I'M CHILEAN,
BUT I FEEL LIKE MAYBE
I COULD BE SOMETHING ELSE.
I COULD BE MAYBE AN INDIAN
OR AN ALIEN.
BUT I WOULD LOVE TO KNOW
FOR MY SAKE
AND ALSO TO KNOW
WHAT MY SON IS.
LIKE, MY SON IS HALF ITALIAN,
HALF CHILEAN,
AND THEN HALF ALIEN?
I DON'T KNOW.
- I CAN GUARANTEE YOU--
I COULD PUT MY LIFE SAVINGS
ON IT--YOU'RE 100% CHILEAN.
- YEAH.
- SHE LOOKS LIKE
THE COUNTRY OF CHILE.
I'M PRETTY SURE
SHE CAME FROM THERE.
- HI.
- OH, YOU'RE BACK.
- FINALLY!
- ♪ WE GOT A SWING SET ♪
♪ WE GOT A SWING SET,
WE GOT A SWING SET ♪
- WHERE'S THE SWING SET?
- OUT IN THE BACK.
LET'S GO BUILD THE THING.
- HE WAS WATCHING YOU LEAVE.
HE SAID, "SEE YOU LATER!"
- DUDE.
HE WALKS SO COOL.
- [laughs]
- CAN YOU JUST WALK LIKE HIM,
PLEASE?
- IT'S LIKE, UH...
- LIKE, THERE SHOULD BE
HAPPY MUSIC,
LIKE ♪ DAH DAH DAH DAH DAH ♪
- IT'S HIS ONE HIP
THAT, LIKE, POPS.
- OH...[bleep].
- DOES THIS REALLY COME
WITH TOOLS?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- WELL, THIS IS STEP ONE
RIGHT HERE.
"MAXIMUM VERTICAL FALL HEIGHT."
6'5".
THAT WOULD KILL YOU.
- OH, MY GOD.
- DUDE, WE'RE GONNA BE HERE
A WHILE.
DEFINITELY, THIS THING IS HARDER
TO PUT TOGETHER THAN I THOUGHT.
IT'S LIKE LITERALLY 20 BOARDS
AND 1,900 SCREWS, BOLTS,
YOU KNOW, NUTS, WASHERS,
AND IT'S...
IT'S CRAZY TO PUT
THIS THING TOGETHER.
THIS IS A [bleep] NIGHTMARE.
- THIS IS THE ONE I TOOK OUT.
- ROGER!
THE BABY POOPED.
- POOPED?
- YOU GOTTA CHANGE HIS DIAPER.
- OKAY. JIONNI CAN DO THIS.
- THIS IS A TEST.
THIS IS A TEST FOR ROGER.
LET'S SEE IF HE CAN
PUT A SWING SET TOGETHER
AND TAKE CARE OF LORENZO.
- WHAT'S MY LITTLE MAN DOING?
- THIS IS WHAT PARENTHOOD'S
ALL ABOUT.
WE'RE PUTTING YOU
TO THE TEST.
- ROGER, LORENZO'S HUNGRY!
- OKAY.
- [imitating airplane]
- OH, MY GOD! YAY!
- THEN TWO G4s GO THROUGH HERE--
- ROGER!
- YEAH.
- LORENZO NEEDS A BATH.
- ALL RIGHT.
- JIONNI, LOOK HOW CUTE
ROGER'S BEING!
- ROGER, LORENZO THREW UP
EVERYWHERE!
- YOU NEED ME RIGHT NOW?
- WELCOME TO MY WORLD.
- ROGER!
- BABE--
- LOVE YOU.
- CAN YOU LOCK THAT DOOR
BEHIND YOU?
- ROGER, LORENZO NEEDS TO CHANGE
HIS DIAPER AGAIN.
- LORENZO'S CRYING.
- LORENZO NEEDS HIS JAMMIES ON.
ROGER!
- ROGER!
- THAT GOES UP HERE.
- ROGER, LORENZO POOPED.
CHANGE HIS DIAPER.
HE WANTS TO PUNCH US ALL
IN THE FACE.
- IS IT NORMAL?
DOES A KID [bleep] THAT MUCH?
- HE'S GONNA KILL ME!
HE HAD THAT MEAN WALK.
- [high voice]
LET'S GO, BUDDY, OH!
THIS IS THE LIFE
RIGHT HERE, KIDS.
- MM-HMM.
- DOESN'T GET ANY BETTER
THAN THIS.
[Lorenzo crying]
AW.
- BABE.
GO. YOU GOTTA GO.
- I HEAR LORENZO CRYING
IN THE BACKGROUND.
I'M NOT GONNA TAKE THIS LIGHTLY.
I'M GONNA TAKE THIS SERIOUS.
[Lorenzo fussing]
- SHH, SLEEPY SLEEPIES.
SHH.
SHH, SLEEPY SLEEPIES.
SHH, SHH.
- IT'S CLEAR SHE TRUSTS ME,
AND I DON'T THINK
SHE'S LIKE THAT WITH MANY PEOPLE
WHEN IT COMES TO HER SON.
- YOU WENT
THROUGH BOOT CAMP TODAY.
YOU HELPED ME ALL DAY.
YOU DID A LOT.
IS THERE ANY CHANCE
OF YOU GETTING LUCKY
IN OUR EXTRA BEDROOM?
- [laughs] NO! MY GOD, NO!
- I HAD DAIRY.
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- HER STOMACH HURTS.
SHE HAS GAS.
- THANK YOU.
- WOULDN'T MATTER
WHAT SHE ATE, DUDE.
- THANKS, BABE.
- YOU'RE KILLING ME, GIRL.
YOU NEED TO SEE A DOCTOR
AND UP YOUR LIBIDO SOMEHOW.
- NO, YOU NEED TO BE
MORE ROMANTIC.
- YOU NEED VIAGRA FOR WOMEN
IF THEY MAKE IT.
- NO.
- IF I GET YOU DRUNK,
IS THERE ANY CHANCE
OF GETTING LUCKY?
- YES!
SHE WANTS IT TO BE...
- OUT IN THE TRUCK?
- TEN MINUTES,
NICE AND SENSUAL.
NOT LIKE...
AND--PFFT!
- I FEEL LIKE
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
- YOU GUYS SHOULD JUST
TRY LOVE ONCE.
- DIDN'T YOU ASK HER TO--
- OH, COME ON.
YOU'VE MADE LOVE BEFORE?
I SWEAR TO GOD!
- YES!
- YOU GUYS HAVE MADE LOVE?
- BEAUTIFUL, ROG.
IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
- HOW DO YOU MAKE LOVE?
WHAT DO YOU DO?
- IT'S JUST...
- YOU JUST GOTTA FEEL IT.
- WHO MAKES LOVE?
REALLY?
ROMEO AND JULIET?
- THEY KILLED THEMSELVES.
- YEAH, THERE YOU GO.
PROBABLY FROM LOVEMAKING.
WHY, ARE YOU GUYS
GONNA HAVE SEX TONIGHT?
IF YOU ARE,
DO YOU MIND IF I WATCH?
- OH, MY GOD.
- [laughing]
- SERIOUSLY.
EW.
- ♪ SO TAKE ALL THAT FEELING ♪
- I WISH EVERY NIGHT
WAS LIKE THIS.
- RIGHT?
- IT'S SO FUN.
- IT COULD BE.
- WHO'S DOING THE DISHES?
- I'LL MOVE IN WITH MY DOGS.
- THE GIRLS.
- THE DISHWASHER.
- NICE ANSWER, NICOLE.
- I WANNA PUT MY ONESIE ON.
- OOH! I'M FULL.
- ROGER, BOOT CAMP
AIN'T OVER, BUDDY.
LET'S GO BUILD
THE SWING SET HERE.
[Roger laughing]
- UGH.
IT'S DARK OUT THERE.
- OH, MY GOD, CAN YOU?
CAN YOU?
OH, MY GOD, HE PICKED ROGER UP!
- OH, MY GOD!
- JIONNI, DON'T BREAK
YOUR BACK, PLEASE!
- OH, MY GOD, BABE.
- DUDE, ROGER'S LIKE
300 POUNDS.
- DON'T HURT MY FUTURE HUSBAND.
[Roger laughing]
- YOU KNOW YOU COULD
BREAK YOUR BACK.
HE'S LIKE A MILLION POUNDS.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK I AM,
A LITTLE SHRIMP?
- NO, JIONNI!
I KNEW HE WAS GONNA SAY THAT.
- SO THAT LINES UP
WITH THE BOTTOM BOTTOM...
- BUT WE'RE SURE
IT'S ON THE RIGHT SIDE, THOUGH?
- NO.
- THIS IS LITERALLY LIKE
DANNY DEVITO
AND ARNOLD SCHWARZENEGGER
RIGHT NOW.
- BUT THEY LOOK LIKE ME AND YOU.
- [laughs] I KNOW!
- SO HERE'S WHAT
I NEED YOU TO DO
AS I READ THESE OFF.
YOU'RE GONNA FIND THE TOP--
- [laughs]
- TURN AROUND.
[dance music]
YOU LOOK LIKE [bleep]
TELETUBBIES GONE BAD.
[both laughing]
- YOU WERE HOT.
- THANKS.
- LET'S BE REAL.
YOU LOOK GOOD
IN A GARBAGE BAG.
- THANKS! YOU TOO.
- THANK YOU.
- IT'LL BE 3:00 A.M.
BEFORE WE GET THIS DONE.
- DO YOU NEED HELP?
- ALL RIGHT,
YOU GUYS COME WORK ON THIS.
- LET'S HELP THEM.
- WATCHING THE SWING SET
GETTING BUILT,
I'M JUST LIKE--UGH!
I DON'T KNOW HOW
IT'S SUPPOSED TO LOOK,
BUT I KNOW IT'S GONNA
TAKE FOREVER.
THEY JUST NEED HELP.
- DOES ANYTHING
LOOK RIGHT ABOUT THAT?
- PSHH!
- NICOLE,
GET WITH THE PROGRAM.
- YOU HAVE THE DIRECTIONS,
NOT ME.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- HERE YOU GO.
PUT THAT ONE OVER THERE.
- YES, MASTER.
- JENNI, YOU GOTTA
SCREW THEM IN.
- UM, I'M STILL
COLLECTING MY WOOD.
- IT'S THE FIRST TIME I'VE SEEN
HER HANDLE WOOD IN THREE YEARS.
- HA HA HA HA.
- NICOLE, WHAT IN GOD'S
[bleep] EARTH ARE YOU DOING?
- I'M LOOKING FOR ALIENS.
I HEARD A PLANET.
- AND THEY WILL SHOOT YOUR HEAD
OFF WITH A LASER BEAM.
- NO.
- OKAY.
- THAT'S JUST IN STAR WARS.
- THEY WERE STORM TROOPERS,
NOT ALIENS.
- I'D RATHER BE WITH AN ALIEN.
- OKAY.
GO HANG OUT WITH YOUR ALIENS.
ARE WE FIGHTING?
- YEAH.
COME SEE THIS.
- HA HA HA!
- HANG ON, IT'S SORT--
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THE GROUND MIGHT BE OFF.
- NO.
- NO, IT'S THE PIECE OF WOOD.
- YEAH, THAT'S CROOKED
AS A MOTHER[bleep].
- MAYBE IT'S SUPPOSED TO HAVE
A LITTLE CROOKEDNESS TO IT.
- JUST CALL BOB THE BUILDER.
- WHO'S BOB?
- THE BUILDERS.
WE'RE NOT GENIUSES.
[laughter]
- HORRENDOUS.
- WHO WANTS TO CALL IT QUITS?
- ME!
- ME.
- LIKE, I'M SO HAPPY
THAT THE BOYS WENT OUT
AND GOT LORENZO A SWING SET.
THAT'S AMAZING.
BUT YOU NEED A PROFESSIONAL.
THIS IS WHAT THEY DO.
THIS IS THEIR JOB.
BUT, HEY,
WHO LISTENS TO ME EVER?
GO TO BED NOW.
- THANKS FOR HELPING.
- LET ME GRAB THAT BOOTY
OF YOURS.
- THANKS. REMIND ME
TO NEVER DO THIS AGAIN.
- THERE'S MORE SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW
ON THE WAY...
- AND IT CONTINUES NOW.
OOH!
WANNA GO WAKE UP JENNI
AND ROGER?
SO IT'S THE MORNING
AFTER BABY BOOT CAMP,
AND I THINK ROGER DID
AN EXCELLENT JOB LAST NIGHT.
BUT I FEEL LIKE IT'S STILL
THE BABY BOOT CAMP,
SO WHY NOT WAKE ROGER
AND JENNI UP WITH LORENZO?
BECAUSE YOU CAN'T BE PISSED
AT LORENZO FOR WAKING YOU UP.
- HEY. WHAT YOU DOING, BUDDY?
- DADDY DUTIES.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M A LITTLE TIRED TODAY,
YOU KNOW?
LAST NIGHT WAS A ROUGH NIGHT
PUTTING TOGETHER THE SWING SET,
BUT, I MEAN,
HOW CAN YOU NOT WAKE UP
WITH A SMILE ON YOUR FACE
WHEN YOU GOT LORENZO, YOU KNOW,
RIGHT THERE WHEN YOU WAKE UP,
RIGHT IN YOUR FACE?
YOU HUNGRY?
[imitates airplane]
AH, THAT'S THE KEY.
- THERE YOU GO.
- I GOT IT.
WE JUST GOTTA PUT IT
ON YOUR PLATE.
- YEAH, HE'S A BIG BOY NOW.
I HONESTLY THINK ROGER,
DEEP DOWN,
IS LIKE A CUDDLE BEAR,
LIKE HE'S A TEDDY BEAR
EVEN THOUGH HE LOOKS,
LIKE, BIG AND SCARY.
HE'S GOT THESE MUSCLES.
HE LOOKS LIKE A JUICE HEAD.
I HAVE NO DOUBT THAT HE WOULD BE
AN AMAZING FATHER.
JIONNI, WE SHOULD GIVE ROGER
A REPORT CARD.
- YEAH.
- I PERSONALLY THINK
YOU DID AWESOME.
I'M IMPRESSED.
I'M SO HAPPY.
- "C," "B," OR "A"?
- YOU'RE GONNA BE A GREAT DADDY.
A-PLUS. YEAH.
- A-PLUS?
- YOU DID A GREAT JOB,
TO BE HONEST.
- I LOVE THIS TIME
WITH LORENZO RIGHT NOW.
AND I'M SO GLAD ROGER
FELL IN LOVE WITH HIM
JUST AS MUCH AS I FELL
IN LOVE WITH HIM.
DOING WHAT HE JUST DID SHOWS
THAT HE'LL BE A GREAT PARENT.
- HE'S SO ADORABLE.
[Lorenzo babbles]
[Lorenzo babbling]
- I FEEL GOOD NOW, MAN.
I'M CHANGED.
- YOU WANNA GIVE IT A SHOT?
- WE'LL JUST CALL A PROFESSIONAL
TO BUILD THE SWING SET.
- CALL SOMEBODY?
- YES.
- YEAH.
THE SWING SET'S
NOT GONNA GET BUILT.
- I THINK THE BOYS--
THEY PUT IN GREAT EFFORT,
AND THEY REALLY TRIED
TO BUILD THE SWING SET, BUT...
- I'M NOT WASTING ANOTHER DAY.
- HELL, NO.
THIS IS A JOB
FOR THE PROFESSIONALS.
[line ringing]
- [grunts]
- GENERAL CONTRACTORS.
HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
- I HAVE A SWING SET HERE
THAT I STARTED,
AND I MIGHT NEED SOME HELP
PUTTING IT TOGETHER.
- OKAY. YEAH, WE DO
SWING SETS ALL THE TIME.
- ALL RIGHT, BABE, THEY LOOK
LIKE THEY'RE IN GOOD HANDS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YOU WANNA GET OUT OF HERE?
- LORENZO, SAY BYE.
SAY, "THANK YOU
FOR TAKING CARE OF ME."
ROGER DID A GREAT JOB.
- BYE, BUDDY.
- LOVE YOU.
- I'M EXACTLY ON THE SAME PAGE
AS I WAS BEFORE BABY BOOT CAMP.
I DO WANT BABIES ONE DAY,
BUT JUST NOT TOMORROW.
BUT YET IF I KNEW THAT I WAS
GONNA HAVE A SON LIKE THAT,
I MIGHT PLANT THAT SEED
TOMORROW.
THAT COULD BE A WHOLE PROCESS
IN AND OF ITSELF,
HAVING JENNI TALK--
I'D HAVE TO GET HER DRUNK.
LET'S BE HONEST.
- HOW DO YOU THINK YOU DID
WITH LORENZO, BABY?
- I FEEL LIKE
LORENZO IS DEFINITELY
THE EXCEPTION TO THE RULE.
HE'S LIKE THE PERFECT BABY,
YOU KNOW?
I DON'T THINK THAT
WE'RE EVER GONNA BE THAT BLESSED
TO HAVE A CHILD
THAT ACTS THAT WELL.
- I WOULDN'T SAY THAT, THOUGH,
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE
IF WE GAVE OUR CHILD
LOVE AND AFFECTION
LIKE THEY DO...
- WHAT ABOUT HIJACKING HIM?
WE COULD DO THAT.
- GOD, YOUR [bleep]
SENSE OF HUMOR REALLY JUST--
- [laughing]
[Lorenzo babbling]
- DADA!
OUR SWING SET'S DONE.
THE SWING SET IS DONE,
AND I WANT TO TELL ROGER
AND JENNI, "I TOLD YOU SO,"
BECAUSE I SAID BEFORE
WE NEED PROFESSIONALS,
AND NO ONE LISTENED TO ME.
[Lorenzo shrieks]
- SWING SET, SWING SET,
SWING SET, SWING SET.
- I THINK MOMMY'S MORE EXCITED
THAN YOU ARE.
SWING SET!
- SWING SET...
- WOW!
- OH, MY GOD!
DADA--IT'S YOUR SWING SET!
YOUR DAD BUILT THIS FOR YOU!
- OKAY.
- YEAH, DADA.
ONE...TWO...
THREE!
- WHEE!
[Lorenzo babbling]
OH!
- YEAH, DADA!
- IS THAT HAPPY OR SAD?
- HE LOVES IT.
- HE'S JUST SO HAPPY,
AND HE DESERVES A SWING SET.
- IT FEELS SO GOOD SEEING
YOUR SON SMILE LIKE THIS.
- MM, I LOVE HIM.
- OH.
- I LOVE HIM.
- THIS IS YOURS.
- IT'S YOURS!
- NO ONE CAN TAKE IT AWAY
FROM YOU.
EVERY BOY SHOULD CARVE HIS NAME
INTO THE SWING SET.
I MEAN, I SURE DID
WHEN I WAS A KID.
HE OWNS IT, IT'S HIS,
AND IT'S JUST COOL.
- LOOK, HE'S LAUGHING!
IT JUST MAKES ME REALLY EXCITED
THAT WE'RE A FAMILY,
AND IT MAKES ME EXCITED
BECAUSE NOW I WANT MORE BABIES.
LIKE, I LOVE THIS FEELING.
WHATEVER.
I GIVE UP.
- IT'S NOT BLOOD WORK, RIGHT?
I AM GOING
TO THE DNA TESTING PLACE.
THERE'S A POSSIBILITY THAT I
COULD BE FROM ANOTHER PLANET.
- DO YOU GO
THROUGH THE KISSING,
THE TOUCHING?
- CARESSING.
- [laughing]
I CAN'T DEAL WITH YOU.
- WHY DON'T WE START
THE SOUFFLE?
- I THINK WE SHOULD
COOK FRENCH.
♪ FRERE JACQUES ♪
- IF YOU DON'T GET LAID
AFTER THIS NIGHT,
FORGET ABOUT IT.