- I CIRCLED THE SECTIONS
YOU NEED TO WORK ON
TO GET THEM PAST THE TEST.
- AS LONG AS IT MAKES
MY DOGS BETTER.
HOW'S YOUR LITTLE BABY?
- HE STILL LIKES JIONNI MORE.
- YOU KNOW THAT MOMMY DATE THING
THAT THEY DO?
ME AND LORENZO NEED
TO START BONDING
LIKE HE BONDS WITH JIONNI.
SINCE I'M ADOPTED,
I REALLY WANT TO GET
A DNA TEST.
I WOULD LIKE TO KNOW
WHAT I AM,
SO I CAN TELL MY SON
ONE DAY.
THERE'S A POSSIBILITY
THAT I COULD BE
FROM ANOTHER PLANET,
LIKE I'M AN ALIEN.
- OH, GIRL.
- JOEY!
- [laughing] SHUT UP!
- NOW IT'S GONNA BE
A PARTY.
- MY NIPPLE'S OUT.
- [laughs]
[Icona Pop's I Love It]
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* *
* I DON'T CARE *
[techno music]
[line ringing]
* *
- HI.
- HI. WHAT YOU DOING?
- NOTHING.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- NOTHING. BORED.
I FEEL LIKE I NEED
A GAY JOEY NIGHT.
- I HAD SUCH A GOOD TIME
TRYING ON DRESSES
WITH THE JOEYS.
- HELL, YEAH.
- AND I FEEL LIKE
WE'VE ONLY SEEN THEM ONCE
THIS SUMMER,
SO I THINK WE NEED TO HAVE
A GAY JOEY NIGHT.
- SERIOUSLY.
- MM-HMM.
- IT'S PAST DUE.
DID YOU SAY "PESTO"?
- PAST DUE.
- OH, I THOUGHT SHE WAS LIKE,
"PESTO."
- COULD YOU IMAGINE?
A GAY-JOEY-PALOOZA,
AND THEN ON TOP OF IT,
INVITING KURTIS.
- I'M TOTALLY DOWN FOR THAT.
I LOVE DRAG QUEENS,
AND I LOVE KURTIS.
- KURTIS/MISS FAME
IS ONE OF MY DEAR FRIENDS.
HE'S, LIKE,
MY NUMBER ONE DRAG STAR.
SO I THINK WE HAVE TO GET
DRAG QUEEN
SUPERSTAR MAKEOVERS.
- WELL, MAYBE WE CAN INVITE THEM
TO YOUR HOUSE
AND THROW
A FUN GAY JOEY PARTY.
- UGH, I NEED THAT
IN MY LIFE.
- ME TOO.
ALL RIGHT, I LOVE YOU.
BYE.
- BYE.
- * WHY CAN'T YOU SEE *
* I NEED SOMEONE'S
HELPING HAND *
- A JOEY DAY?
- A JOEY DAY,
TURNING INTO NIGHT,
AND NICOLE
AND MAYBE KURTIS--
MISS FAME.
MY JOEY
THAT I GREW UP WITH
ALWAYS WANTED TO KNOW
WHAT IT FELT LIKE
TO BE IN DRAG,
AND I FEEL LIKE TONIGHT
WOULD BE THE PERFECT NIGHT
TO DRESS UP
LIKE WE DID AS KIDS
AND BECAME FABULOUS DRAG STARS.
- DO YOU MIND
IF I DO SOMETHING ELSE?
- NO, WHY DON'T YOU JOIN?
- IT'S NOT REALLY
MY THING, JENNI.
- I KNOW.
- I'LL GO DO SOMETHING
WITH JIONNI OR SOMETHING.
- OKAY, THAT'S FINE.
- I'M SURE THAT'S NOT
HIS CUP OF TEA EITHER, SO--
I LOVE THE GAY JOEYS.
I JUST CHOOSE NOT
TO BE PART
OF THE GAY GAGA-PALOOZA
THAT'S ABOUT TO HAPPEN.
HEY! LEAVE HER ALONE.
- SIT!
- KNOCK IT OFF.
- WHAT?
I AM VERY OVERWHELMED TODAY.
MY BABIES GOTTA TAKE
THEIR, YOU KNOW,
FINAL EXAM
TO BE SERVICE DOGS.
BASICALLY, I'M PRAYING
THAT BELLA JUST PASSES.
[line ringing]
- WHAT'S UP, MAN?
- JENNI JUST TOLD ME
THAT ALL THE JOEYS
ARE COMING DOWN.
DO YOU FEEL LIKE DOING
SOMETHING?
- YO, I THINK TODAY'S
A GOOD DAY
TO GO FISHING, MAN.
IT'S WAY TOO NICE OUT.
- CALL YOUR MOM
OR SOMEONE LIKE THAT
AND GET A SITTER.
- SOUNDS GOOD.
MAYBE WE CAN CATCH
SOME REAL FISH,
NOT LIKE YOU DID AT...
- CHERNOBYL LAKE?
- THE DUDE RANCH.
CHERNOBYL LAKE.
- ALL RIGHT, BUDDY.
- BYE.
- LATER.
[upbeat rock music]
- * LET'S GO TO SWIM CLASS *
YOU WENT POOPY.
I SMELL IT.
[whimsical music]
OOH, DID YOU LEAVE ME
A LITTLE PRESENT?
DID YOU LEAVE ME
OH, YOU STINK.
HE'S GONNA HATE ME
WHEN HE'S, LIKE, 16.
LIKE, "WHY WOULD YOU TALK
ABOUT MY POOP LIKE THAT?"
* *
OH, MY GOD, HE STINKS.
OOH!
SOMEONE WENT POOPIES
IN THEIR PANTS.
HI.
- HI!
- HE JUST TOOK A BIG [bleep].
HE STINKS.
- [laughing]
OH, NO.
BETTER THAN IN THE POOL.
- IT'S YOUR FRIEND.
- HI! ARE YOU HAPPY
ABOUT THAT?
- YOU SMELL HIM?
- OH!
- OH, GOD.
- HE'S STINKIES.
I GOTTA GO CHANGE
HIS DIAP-DIAPS.
- YOU READY TO GO?
OOH, THERE IT IS, YEAH.
- OH, YOU SEE IT?
[bleep].
- NO, I CAN SMELL HIM.
- OH.
- * I AM EXACTLY
WHO I WANT TO BE *
- WHO'S EXCITED?
BELLA, ARE YOU GONNA PASS?
ARE YOU GONNA PASS
WITH MOMMY?
CLEARLY, I HOPE MY DOGS
DO BETTER AT SCHOOL
THAN MOMMY DID.
THEY'RE GONNA BE
SERVICE DOGS.
THEN THEY CAN GO EVERYWHERE.
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE
MOMMY PROUD.
WHO'S THAT?
- HI, HONEY.
HEY, BEAUTIFUL.
- HI.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD, HOW ARE YOU?
- YOU LOOK WONDERFUL. GREAT.
- OOP, OOP, I GOT A POOPER.
- WHOA!
IF YOUR DOG DEFECATES
IN THE THERAPY AREA,
AUTOMATIC FAIL.
- THIS IS TERRIBLE.
WE HAVEN'T EVEN STARTED
THE TEST,
AND DIESEL'S ALREADY FAILED.
MY EXPECTATIONS WENT
RIGHT OUT THE DOOR.
HE ONLY DOES THAT ON GRASS.
- OH, MY GOD.
OH, IT SMELLS LIKE
A DEAD BODY.
WHEW!
I'M CHANGING
LORENZO'S DIAPER,
AND IT JUST LOOKS LIKE
A [bleep] CRIME SCENE.
THERE'S JUST POOP
EVERYWHERE.
IT'S UP HIS BACK.
AND THIS IS, LIKE,
YOU KNOW,
THIS IS NOT A NORMAL POOP.
IT'S JUST A CRAZY POOP.
WE'RE READY.
- THAT'S A CUTE SUIT.
- OH, THERE'S LORENZO!
DO YOU WANT TO TRY
AND HAVE HIM GO UNDER?
- SURE.
- DO YOU WANT TO SWIM?
- I DEFINITELY DON'T WANT
TO DUNK LORENZO UNDERWATER.
THE POINT OF ME AND LORENZO
GOING TO THESE CLASSES
IS BECAUSE WE'RE TRYING
TO BOND.
SO I'M JUST LIKE,
JACQUELINE,
YOU NEED TO DO IT,
BECAUSE IF I DO IT,
HE'S GONNA FREAK OUT.
- ONE, TWO, THREE.
BRRRRRRRR!
YAY!
both: YAY!
- YOU DID IT!
I'M SO PROUD OF HIM.
HE'S JUST AWESOME.
- DO YOU WANT TO GET
YOUR REPORT CARD?
- YES!
- YOU WANNA SEE?
THIS IS YOUR REPORT CARD
WITH YOUR--
ALL THE STUFF YOU LEARNED.
- YAY!
HE DOESN'T CARE.
- [laughs]
- HE HAS NO IDEA
WHAT'S GOING ON.
- THIS IS
THE OBEDIENCE PORTION.
I NEED YOU
TO HAVE THE DOG SIT.
- SIT.
BELLA, SIT.
SIT!
[dog barks]
- YOU CAN'T TOUCH THE DOG
WHEN YOU'RE DOING THIS.
- LAY DOWN.
LAY DOWN.
LAY DOW--NO.
[dog barking]
LAY DOWN.
LAY DOWN. LAY DOWN!
- ALL RIGHT.
- DOWN.
- WE GOTTA STOP, OKAY?
- NO, PHIL,
I HAD SUCH HIGH HOPES.
GO BACK.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHY BELLA
ISN'T LYING DOWN
OR DOING ANYTHING,
AND THEN I REMEMBER, OH,
'CAUSE SHE'S A DIVA,
AND SHE DOESN'T DO ANYTHING
WITHOUT A TREAT.
LIKE I TAUGHT HER,
NO TRICKS
WITHOUT TREATS, BABY.
NOW IT'S BITING ME
IN THE ASS.
- SHE'S NOT READY.
THAT'S ALL.
- AND IF SHE CAN'T PASS,
NOEL SURE AS HELL AIN'T PASSING.
- THIS IS A TEST
OF STABILITY.
SHE'S GOT
TO OVERRIDE DISTRACTIONS.
OKAY, READY?
GO AHEAD.
- READY?
[pans clanging]
YAY!
[dog barking]
- ALL RIGHT, SHE WAS CLEARLY,
"LET'S GET OUTTA HERE."
- I SHOULD'VE CHEATED
AND PUT, LIKE,
PEANUT BUTTER OR SOMETHING
ON MY FINGERS,
SO AT LEAST I KNOW BELLA
WOULD [bleep] PASS.
WHY DON'T I CHEAT?
I CHEATED ALL THROUGH
HIGH SCHOOL, [bleep].
- UNFORTUNATELY, UM,
BASED ON TODAY,
ALL THREE DOGS DID HAVE TO FAIL.
- MY DOGS ARE ALL FAILURES.
ALL THREE OF THEM.
NOT EVEN CLOSE.
MY LITTLE FAILURES.
YOU ALL FAILED.
I REALLY WISH MY DOGGIES
WOULD HAVE PASSED.
THEY WOULD'VE LOOKED SO CUTE
IN THE ORANGE JACKETS.
BUT I'M GONNA STICK TO IT,
AND THE ULTIMATE GOAL
IS TO HAVE THEM
AS PERFECT ANGELS THAT
I CAN WALK INTO THE NAIL SALON,
AND THEY ALL SIT IN A ROW
LIKE THEY'RE LITTLE STATUES.
I'LL TELL YOU THIS--
I WILL NEVER HAVE THREE KIDS.
[hip-hop music]
- MY LITTLE FAILURES.
* *
I FEEL LIKE,
SINCE IT IS DRAG NIGHT,
WE SHOULD HAVE
A DRAG SIGNATURE DRINK.
- OKAY.
* *
- HELLO?
- OH, THAT'S MINE.
100% HE'S WASTED.
- AND WE JUST ORDERED FOOD.
- WHO'S COMING?
THE OTHER BOYS
ARE COMING, RIGHT?
- TWO JOEYS AND MISS FAME.
YOU KNOW KURTIS, RIGHT?
- YES, YES, YES, YES.
- YEAH.
- I WAS GONNA SURPRISE THEM ALL
AT THE SAME TIME.
- OH. DON'T SAY ANYTHING.
- DON'T SAY ANYTHING.
- ABOUT KURTIS?
- YEAH. SHH.
- I HAVE TO MAKE YOU
OUR DRAG DRINKS.
- THERE'S A DRAG QUEEN COMING.
- WHO?
- KURTIS.
- OH, MISS FAME?
- WAIT, WHY ARE YOU--
- JOEY!
- WE SAID DON'T TELL HIM!
- WHAT THE [bleep]?
- CAN'T TELL YOU ANYTHING.
[hip-hop music]
* *
- WHAT ARE YOU BAITING UP WITH,
CLAMS?
- OOH-AHH!
- OH, I GOT CRABS.
CRABS TOOK MY BAIT--
ONE OF 'EM.
- UH-OH.
- WHAT?
- PROBABLY A LITTLE BAITFISH.
- TOUGH ONE TO BRING IN.
HO!
- OH, THAT'S A--
- [laughing]
YEAH!
- THAT'S A LITTLE SEA BASS,
ISN'T IT?
- YEAH!
- GOOD JOB,
YOU SON OF A [bleep].
- ALL RIGHT!
I HOOK A SEA BASS
IN A MATTER OF MINUTES.
IT'S THAT EASY.
BEATING ROGER IS THAT EASY.
- HERE'S HOW I LOOK AT IT.
IF YOU PUT A BIG ENOUGH HUNK
OF MEAT ON THERE,
NOT GONNA [bleep] AROUND
WITH THE LITTLE FISH.
- WHY DO YOU DO TWO HOOKS?
- TWICE THE CHANCE
OF CATCHING SOMETHING, BUDDY.
YO, I GOT SOMETHING.
- GOT IT?
- YEP.
- HE'S GOT SOMETHING!
[suspenseful music]
- OH, THIS IS A GOOD SIZE.
WATCH OUT, I WANNA GET--
- WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
- I DON'T WANT IT HUNG UP
ON THE MOTOR.
IT'S A GOOD-SIZED FISH.
- WHAT IS THAT?
- IT'S A FLUKE.
- IT'S A SHARK. IT'S A SHARK!
- NO, IT'S A DOGFISH.
- YEAH!
- DOGFISH.
* *
- THAT'LL BAIT 'EM?
- YEAH, IT'S A DOGFISH.
- WHAT'S A DOGFISH?
- SHARK.
- I'M CONFUSED.
A DOG SHARK?
- AHH. WHAT DO YOU THINK
THE GIRLS ARE DOING RIGHT NOW
WITH THE JOEYS?
- BEING VERY, VERY,
VERY, VERY GAY.
- [laughs]
- WHEN YOU'RE WITH THE JOEYS,
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS.
- IT'S WHAT HAPPENS.
- A SIDE OF MEATBALLS, LOOK.
- JOEY!
- I HAVE A SURPRISE FOR YOU.
- WHAT?
WHAT?
- MISS FAME'S COMING DOWN...
- STOP.
- TO GIVE ALL OF US,
ESPECIALLY YOU,
THE ULTIMATE DRAG MAKEOVER.
- [laughing]
[all exclaiming]
- OH, MY GOD.
- I KNOW HOW MUCH
YOU'VE WANTED THIS.
- YES, I'M READY.
- YOU READY?
- YES.
- * ARE YOU READY FOR THIS? *
- * YES *
* *
* YES, YES *
- DOES KURTIS HAVE
A BOYFRIEND?
- KURTIS JUST GOT MARRIED.
- HE'S MARRIED.
- OH, PERFECT,
SO I'M THE ONLY SINGLE ONE.
AND I'M ALSO FAT.
- [laughing]
JOEY, SHUT UP.
- * YOU READY FOR THIS?
YOU READY FOR THIS? *
- * YES, YES *
- HAVE YOU EVER HAD A--
- HELLO?
- [bleep].
- * YOU READY FOR THIS? *
- MAMA'S HOME!
- HI!
- OH, MY GOD, YOU'RE SO HOT!
- OH, THIS OLD THING, GIRL?
JUST ROLLED OUT OF BED.
MWAH!
- SHE'S HOTTER THAN US.
- SERIOUSLY.
- MAKES ME FEEL UGLY.
- LEGS TO DIE FOR.
- I HAVE
THE WORST STOMACHACHE.
MY BALLS ARE
INSIDE MY ASS.
[laughter]
[peaceful music]
- SO LET ME ASK YOU,
THE ADOPTION STUFF,
YOU GUYS EVER TALK ABOUT IT
AT ALL?
- YEAH, I MEAN, BASICALLY,
WE DON'T KNOW WHERE WE STAND
RIGHT NOW
ON HAVING KIDS,
AND WE'RE UP IN THE AIR
KIND OF ON EVERYTHING--
MARRIAGE, KIDS,
THE WHOLE NINE YARDS.
YOU KNOW, MY BIGGEST FEAR
IS FAILING AS A FATHER.
THAT'S WHY I'M
ALMOST 40 YEARS OLD,
AND I'VE NEVER DONE IT.
- YEAH, IT'S A DIFFERENT--
IT'S A DIFFERENT WORLD.
IT'S ALWAYS A GOOD FEELING
TO HAVE A BABY
WITH YOUR LOVED ONE.
- I'M JUST SCARED.
I'M SCARED TO FAIL.
SO BECAUSE OF THAT, I'VE ALWAYS
GONE WITH THE SAFE ROUTE,
AND THE SAFE ROUTE
IS NOT HAVING ANY.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I'VE DEFINITELY NOTICED
THAT JENNI
IS FLIP-FLOPPING
A LITTLE LATELY,
ESPECIALLY WITH SPENDING
SO MUCH TIME WITH NICOLE.
YOU KNOW, WEDDING PLANNING
AND WEDDING DRESS SHOPPING
AND SAYING, YOU KNOW,
SHE'S MORE INCLINED
TO GET MARRIED NOW.
- GOING TO THE VENUES
AND [bleep].
- MORE WANTING TO HAVE KIDS.
THE OTHER DAY, SHE TOLD ME
SHE WAS OVULATING.
- WELL, GET ON THAT [bleep],
MAN.
- IF SHE REALLY WANTS
TO HAVE A KID,
AND SHE REALLY WANTS
TO GET MARRIED,
I HOPE SHE WOULD JUST
SAY IT.
BUT SHE'LL KIND OF JUST, LIKE,
DROP HINTS
AND SAY IT IN PASSING
WHILE SHE'S DRINKING
AND THEN BLOWS IT OFF
THE NEXT DAY.
JUST LOOK ME IN THE EYES
AND SAY WHAT YOU WANT.
YOU KNOW,
IT'S SO CONFUSING.
I JUST FEEL LIKE
WE'RE NOT READY.
WE'RE NOT IN THAT...
- MAYBE SHE SAW THAT--
- STATE OF MIND
OR THAT STAGE
IN OUR RELATIONSHIP
WHERE WE'RE SOLID ENOUGH
TO COMMIT
TO SOMETHING THAT BIG,
YOU KNOW?
WE STILL HAVE DAYS
WHERE IT'S THIS POWER STRUGGLE
FOR WHO RUNS THE SHOW,
YOU KNOW?
AND SHE WANTS TO RUN
THE SHOW,
AND I WANT TO RUN THE SHOW,
AND YOU CAN ONLY HAVE
ONE CAPTAIN.
- SHALL WE GET
THIS PARTY STARTED?
- YEAH!
- YES!
- OOH!
- OH, MY GOD, I LOVE THIS.
- NEED SOME PROFESSIONAL HELP
WITH THIS.
- OH, MY GOD.
SHAVE YOUR [bleep] FACE, DUDE.
COME ON.
[techno music]
- THESE ARE HEAVY.
JENNI, IS THIS HOW YOU FEEL
EVERY DAY?
- UH-HUH.
- OH, MY GOD.
[techno music]
- CAN YOU GIVE ME BIG LIPS?
- BIG LIPS?
- YEAH, LIKE, RED.
- PARTY IS HERE!
- OH, MY GOD.
- [laughs]
- I NEED AN OUTFIT.
- WHERE IS YOUR WIG?
- YOU LOOK LIKE
AN ATLANTIC CITY HOOKER.
- I'M GONNA [bleep] CHANGE.
[bleep] YOU GUYS.
* *
- MISS [bleep] IS COMING
TO THE PARTY.
* *
- YOU'RE PRETTY!
- OH, MY GOD,
YOU LOOK HOT.
- WE'RE CATWALKING.
- DRAG RUNWAY SHOW!
- * DON'T, DON'T, DON'T *
* DON'T STOP *
- ARMS TO THE SIDE.
THE BLONDE BOMBSHELL.
BODY TO THE FLOOR, HONEY.
- ALL RIGHT, JOEY!
[shrieking]
- * DON'T, DON'T *
- OH, MY GOD,
YOU LOOK LIKE JWOWW.
- WHAT A FAMILY OF DRAG.
- I FEEL LIKE,
OUT OF EVERYBODY,
CLEARLY, MISS FAME HAS
THE BEST WALK.
- GO, GIRL.
- [singing]
- POWERHOUSE, WE TURN AND--
- * YEAH, YEAH *
- OH, HELL, NO!
- [laughs]
- [screams]
- WHAT YOU GONNA DO?
WHAT YOU GONNA DO?
- I'VE NEVER SEEN MISS FAME
BE LIKE--
AND SHE WAS LIKE THAT.
AND I LOVED IT.
- I CAN'T HELP IT.
I'M SUPER MANLY--
AND MY PHONE JUST FELL
OUT OF MY DRESS.
[laughter, squeals]
- HIS BALLS JUST CAME OUT.
- I AM
THE WORST DRAG QUEEN EVER.
- [giggling]
- OH.
I CAN'T TWERK.
IT'S LIKE
A TWERK PARTY RIGHT NOW.
JENNI'S DOING IT!
AAH!
JOEY'S TWERKING.
HIS BALLS ARE OUT.
THEY'RE JIGGLING EVERYWHERE.
- I NEED DISINFECTANT SPRAY.
- YEAH, THERE'S, LIKE,
BALL SWEAT EVERYWHERE.
- UGH.
- MY FRIEND, YOU'RE ABOUT TO GET
TEXAS OIL-RIGGED.
[techno music]
- YOU GO, GIRL.
SHOW 'EM.
- [bleep], THIS IS EXHAUSTING.
I CAN'T EVER BE A STRIPPER.
I'M ALL, WHEW!
* *
- [squeals]
THAT ONE LICKED MY BUTT!
- YO, DO WE EVEN WANT
TO GO IN THERE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- I'M SCARED.
- [laughing]
- TWERKED HER WIG OFF!
- OH, MY GOD.
- ROGER!
- MY BALLS!
- I JUST WALKED INTO
THE ROCKY HORROR PICTURE SHOW.
LET'S BE HONEST.
HOW ARE YOU?
- DO YOU LIKE ME AS A REDHEAD?
- YEAH, YOU LOOK GOOD.
- HI, HOW ARE YOU?
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- DO I LOOK SCARY?
- YEAH.
NICOLE'S IN A LITTLE
TINA TURNER OUTFIT.
SHE LOOKS HOT.
- LOOK AT JOEY!
HE LOOKS SO AWESOME.
- LET'S GO KIKI BY THE POOL.
- EVERYONE'S DRESSED UP
AS DRAGS.
IT'S JUST CRAZINESS
GOING ON.
- [high falsetto]
* OOH-HOO OOH *
- OH, DEAR GOD.
- * OOH OOH OOH *
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE GONNA GO,
MY LADIES.
- AWW.
- SO I KNOW JIONNI'S EXHAUSTED
RIGHT NOW,
AND I'M FEELING
A BIT TIRED.
I LOVE MY JOEYS,
BUT IT'S TIME FOR ME TO LEAVE.
- COOL.
- JOEY, HELP ME.
- HMM?
- JOEY, HELP YOUR JOEY.
- IF I SEE PENIS...
- TAKE IT OFF.
- RIGHT NOW,
I'M GONNA CRY.
- TAKE IT OFF MY FOOT.
- OH, MY GOD.
[screams]
A BALL'S HANGING OUT!
A BALL IS--
- [laughing]
OH, MY GOD!
- OH, MY GOD!
- A BALL'S HANGING OUT!
- YOUR BALLS ARE SO RED.
JENNI, ARE MY BALLS RED?
- NO.
- [laughing]
OH, MY GOD!
AND ON THAT NOTE,
YOU GOTTA GO.
- EW!
I SAW YOUR JOEY'S BALL,
AND THAT OFFICIALLY ENDED
MY NIGHT.
- YEAH. IT HAPPENS.
- LIKE, LITERALLY--
- HE'S A HOT MESS.
- GET IN HERE.
- NO.
- ALL RIGHT, BIG GUY.
- GET IN HERE.
- OH!
- YOU GET HOME SAFELY,
ALL RIGHT?
WE'RE--WE'LL BE--
WHOA, WHOA!
HOLD ON, HOLD--
- I DIDN'T TOUCH ANYTHING!
- WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
HE LIKES TO LINGER
WITH THE HUGS.
- AND HIS BALLS ARE OUT.
- IS THAT TRUE?
WAS IT OUT?
WAS THE BALL OUT?
- [laughing]
I DON'T KNOW.
- I'M GONNA BE [bleep] ANNOYED
IF THE BALL WAS OUT.
[crickets chirping]
- I'M GONNA TRY TO MAKE MONEY
AND HIRE YOU
FOR PROSTITUTION.
- I'M MAKING MONEY
ON THE GRASS, 'CAUSE I'M--
[laughs]
I JUST FELL.
- COME ON, GIRLS!
- [groans]
- GET IN!
- [laughing]
I FELL ON THE [bleep]DAMN LAWN.
OH!
- [clears throat]
- I LOVE THAT YOU LOVE
ALL MY GAY FRIENDS.
- OF COURSE.
WHY WOULDN'T I?
- [whispering]
I HAVE A GREY HAIR.
- WHAT?
- [whispering]
I HAVE A GREY HAIR.
- SO?
- THAT MEANS I'M GETTING OLD.
- IT DOES NOT.
- WE'LL [bleep] GET A NANNY.
WE SHOULD HAVE A KID,
SO MY OVARIES DON'T--
- WHERE IS THIS COMING FROM?
JENNI IS DRUNK.
AND THE REASON HOW I KNOW
JENNI IS DRUNK
IS 'CAUSE SHE'S TALKING
ABOUT HAVING BABIES.
THAT'S HOW YOU KNOW
JENNI'S DRUNK.
YOU'VE NEVER SAID
TO ME SOBER,
"I WANT TO HAVE A KID.
LET'S START."
YOU'VE NEVER SAID THAT
TO ME.
- I WOULDN'T SAY THAT
SOBER OR DRUNK.
- YOU JUST SAID IT.
- I WANT TO HAVE A KID, YES,
BUT IT HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH YOU.
- IT'S VERY CONFUSING
FOR ME WHEN,
80% OF THE TIME,
YOU'RE SOBER,
AND YOU'RE OF THE SAME MIND-SET
THAT I AM,
AND THAT IS, WE WANT
TO DO THAT ONE DAY,
WE WANT TO HAVE KIDS ONE DAY,
BUT WE'RE NOT READY TODAY,
TO YOU TELLING ME
THAT YOU WANT TO HAVE BABIES
AND GET MARRIED.
- I'M A LITTLE INTOXICATED,
BUT I FEEL LIKE
I GOT IT OUT,
AND I'M REALLY ITCHY
IN MY ARMPITS.
[sighs]
- I'M AMAZED A BOOB
DIDN'T JUST POP OUT.
- CAN WE GO TO BED?
[laughs]
- THERE'S MORE SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW
ON THE WAY.
- AND IT CONTINUES NOW.
[laid-back music]
* *
[groans]
TODAY I'M GOING TO PICK UP
MY DNA TEST RESULTS,
AND I'M PRETTY EXCITED.
I'M NERVOUS.
YOUR DOOR IS PRETTY HEAVY.
I FEEL LIKE MY RESULTS
ARE GONNA SAY, LIKE,
I'M SOME SORT OF SPANISH.
YOU KNOW,
SOMETHING THAT MAKES MY SKIN
LOOK THIS DARK NATURALLY.
HELLO.
IF I'M AN ALIEN,
THAT WOULD BE
THE BEST-CASE SCENARIO,
BECAUSE I'VE ALWAYS WANTED
TO BE AN ALIEN.
I FEEL LIKE
I'M FROM ANOTHER PLANET.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I FEEL LIKE
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
- SO THE ANCESTRY
FROM EUROPE THAT YOU HAVE
IS ROMANI,
FROM NORTHWESTERN CROATIA, OKAY?
- WHAT?
- ROMANI IS
AN ETHNIC TRIBE
THAT CAME
OUT OF NORTHERN INDIA, OKAY?
- I'M INDIAN?
- NO, WAIT, WAIT.
- DO I NEED TO WEAR, LIKE,
THAT CIRCLE
ON MY HEAD NOW?
YOU NEED TO TALK,
YOU KNOW, STUPID,
BECAUSE I HAVE NO [bleep] IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
- UM, YOU HAVE
MACEDONIAN ROMANI,
GYPSY...
- I'M A GYPSY.
- SPANISH FROM ANDALUSIA,
A REGION OF SPAIN,
SLOVAKIAN, AND RUSSIAN.
OKAY?
NOW, FROM THE WORLD
POPULATION MATCHES,
YOU HAVE JEWISH,
IBERIAN-AMERICAN--
- STOP.
[laughing]
STOP IT.
STOP.
OH, MY GOD.
- I GOTTA GO ON.
YOU WANTED TO KNOW.
- NO, I'M SCARED.
- MIDDLE-EASTERN...
- WHAT THE [bleep]?
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW THESE COULD BE
MY RESULTS
WHEN I WAS BORN IN CHILE
AND ADOPTED FROM CHILE.
- SOUTH ASIAN,
AND EAST ASIA.
- I'M ASIAN.
- YES.
- COME ON.
ARE YOU SURE
THESE ARE MINE?
I DON'T MIND BEING
PART ASIAN
BECAUSE ASIANS ARE HOT,
AND THEY HAVE THAT THIRD MUSCLE
IN THEIR VAGINA,
AND GUYS LIKE THAT,
SO I FEEL LIKE
JIONNI'S BLESSED.
SO I'M NOT FROM CHILE.
- NO, YOU MIGHT HAVE BEEN BORN
THERE, BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN--
- I'M NOT EVEN CHILEAN.
- OKAY.
- SO WEIRD!
I'M A GYPSY.
[upbeat rock music]
* *
- YOU'RE ALL THOSE THINGS?
- YEAH.
- SLOVAKIA?
- RUSSIA!
- YOU'RE JEWISH.
- [laughs]
[Lorenzo squeals]
NO, JIONNI,
IT'S NOT RELIGIOUS.
- WHAT, DO YOU CELEBRATE
YOM KIPPUR?
- NO, JEWISH IS, LIKE,
A PART OF EUROPE.
- DO WE HAVE TO GET MARRIED
IN, LIKE,
A TEMPLE OR SOMETHING?
- NO, JIONNI.
- SORRY, I DON'T WANT
TO INSULT YOUR--
- YOU PEOPLE?
YOU'RE RUDE.
- SOUTH ASIA. SEE?
OH, MY GOD.
IS THIS 100% FACT?
- YEAH.
I'M A GYPSY.
- OH, MY GOD.
- SO THAT'S WHY I FEEL LIKE
I SENSE ALIENS
AND I SENSE GHOSTS,
BECAUSE I'M A GYPSY.
GYPSIES ARE COOL.
YOU KNOW,
THEY HAVE GOOD FASHION.
THEY'RE, YOU KNOW,
OUTRAGEOUS.
THAT'S ME.
SO IT MAKES SENSE NOW.
LIKE, SOMETIMES
I FEEL PSYCHIC,
AND I PREDICT THINGS,
SO NOW I KINDA GET IT,
BECAUSE I'M A GYPSY.
WE'RE GYPSIES.
HIGH FIVE.
- I WANT TO SEE
YOUR GYPSY DANCE.
OH, FORGET IT.
- [laughing]
- ALL JOKES ASIDE,
EVEN THOUGH NICOLE
IS A RUSSIAN JEWISH GYPSY...
- STOP IT.
- I'M STILL GONNA MARRY YOU,
AND I STILL LOVE YOU.
IS THAT A JOKE?
- WE SHOULD DO COUPLES NIGHT.
IT'S SO NICE TO HAVE THE GANG
BACK TOGETHER.
- BABE, CAN YOU POUR ME
A WINE?
- OH, MY GOD.
- SHE'S BACK.
- DEENA, YOU GOT BIRD [bleep]
RIGHT THERE.
- IT'S ON ME?
- [laughing]
- DEENA JUST SAT
IN BIRD [bleep].
- [laughing]
- HI.
[laughing]
OH, MY GOD!
YOUR FAT ASS BROKE IT.