- OOH!
TODAY I'M GOING TO PICK UP
MY DNA TEST RESULTS.
- YOU HAVE ROMANI, GYPSY.
- I'M A GYPSY.
- YOU HAVE JEWISH AND RUSSIAN.
- EVEN THOUGH NICOLE'S
A RUSSIAN JEWISH GYPSY...
- STOP IT!
- I'M STILL GONNA MARRY YOU
AND I STILL LOVE YOU.
- CAN WE FILL OUT
APPLICATIONS?
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU GUYS ARE HERE.
- I'M GETTING
REALLY BAD DEJA VU RIGHT NOW.
[Icona Pop's I Love It]
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* *
* I DON'T CARE *
- I JUST CHIPPED MY TOOTH
ON THE WAY TO HERE.
- EW.
DO YOU WANT SOME VODKA
TO NUMB IT?
- YEAH.
- SO I FEEL LIKE EVER
SINCE I'VE BECOME A MOM,
I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT TO DO
IN SITUATIONS.
SO I'M LIKE, JENNI,
STEP INTO MY OFFICE,
HERE'S SOME VODKA,
SWISH YOUR MOUTH WITH IT.
MAYBE IT'LL STOP
THE INFECTION
AND IT'LL HELP WITH THE PAIN.
- [bleep] PIECE OF [bleep].
[bleep] TOOTH
GAVE UP ON ME,
GAVE UP ON LIFE.
- I WAS THINKING
WE SHOULD HAVE
THE ROOMIES COME DOWN,
DO, LIKE, A COUPLES NIGHT.
- LIKE STEAKS AND BURGERS
AND STUFF?
- YEAH.
THEN EVERYONE SLEEPS OVER.
COUPLES, I THINK,
WOULD BE THE EASIEST.
I'M USED TO SEEING THE ROOMIES
EVERY SINGLE SUMMER
DOWN THE SHORE,
AND THIS IS THE FIRST SUMMER
THAT WE'RE NOT LIVING
WITH THEM.
SO I FEEL LIKE
THIS IS A MUST
TO HAVE THE ROOMIES
COME OVER.
WE WERE THINKING
YOU AND CHRIS AND SAM AND RON.
- I LIKE THAT.
- WE'LL DO BARBECUE
AT THE HOUSE,
AND THEN WE'LL GO
TO THE BOARDWALK
AND GO TO BEACHCOMBER
AND GET DRUNKIES,
AND THEN YOU CAN SLEEP
OVER HERE.
- OH, YAY!
THAT SOUNDS LIKE A LOT OF FUN.
I CAN'T WAIT TO COME.
I'LL TELL RON,
AND I'LL BRING HIM TOO.
- ALL RIGHT, I LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU. THANKS, D.
- BYE.
- LET'S GO GET
OUR SHOP ON RIGHT NOW,
SO WE CAN GET THAT
OUT OF THE WAY.
- I WILL DRIVE SINCE...
YOUR TOOTH BROKE.
- HO HO HO.
- I WOULD KILL MYSELF
IF I WERE YOU.
- READY?
- LET'S DO THIS!
- HOWDY, GIRLS.
- HI.
- HOWDY.
- CAN WE HAVE EIGHT HAMBURGERS?
- EIGHT.
- AND THEN WE NEED
EIGHT HOT DOGS, PLEASE.
- DO YOU HAVE
HOMEMADE ITALIAN SAUSAGE?
- THAT'S WHAT WE'RE WORKING ON
RIGHT NOW.
- WE CAN HELP.
- I THOUGHT SO--YOU GUYS
KNOW HOW TO MAKE SAUSAGE?
- YEAH, I MEAN, IF--
- YOU GUYS KNOW
HOW TO HANDLE A SAUSAGE?
- YES, WE DO, ACTUALLY.
- I MEAN, WHEN A PRETTY GIRL
COMES IN
AND WANTS TO TOUCH
YOUR SAUSAGE,
YOU GOTTA LET HER, YOU KNOW?
- OH, MY GOD!
- I'M TELLING ROGER.
- YOU CAN COME AND TOUCH
OUR SAUSAGE TOO.
- OH HO HO!
- EW.
YOU'D PROBABLY LIKE THAT.
HE'LL GET SOMETHING.
- SO YOU GUYS GONNA COME GIVE US
A HAND BACK HERE OR WHAT?
- YEAH, WE CAN DO IT.
I'D RATHER JUST DO IT OURSELVES.
- LET'S DO IT OURSELVES.
- WE KNOW
HOW TO HANDLE SAUSAGE.
- ALL DAY, EVERY DAY.
- MM-HMM.
- WE CAN DO THIS.
- YEP.
- NO PROBLEM.
- THIS IS WHAT WE GOT GOING.
- OH, IT LOOKS LIKE MEAT.
- YEAH.
- CAN I SMELL IT?
- SURE, YOU CAN.
- YOU WANNA SMELL
THE SAUSAGE?
I DO TOO.
[gasps]
OH!
- I'M SORRY!
I'M SORRY!
- OH, YOU'RE SORRY
'CAUSE YOU COULDN'T DO IT.
- [squeals]
SO WE'RE IN THE BACK,
AND ADAM'S SHOWING US
HOW TO MAKE A SAUSAGE.
SO FIRST YOU STUFF
ALL THE GROUND MEAT
IN THIS LITTLE TUBE THING,
AND THEN YOU HAVE TO PUT
THE CONDOM ON,
WHICH IS A PIG INTESTINE?
- YEAH.
- OOH!
- [laughs]
- HERE IT COMES.
- IT'S LIKE A BABY!
- IT'S A BABY PEEN.
- COMING OUT OF A VAGINE.
- NO! YOU'RE GOING TOO FAST,
I FEEL.
- OH.
WHOA, JENNI!
WHY DON'T YOU DO THIS
TO ROGER?
- HOW DO YOU KNOW I DON'T?
- WE ARE DOING A GREAT JOB
HANDLING THIS MEAT.
- I AM A PROFESSIONAL
AT HANDLING MEAT.
- YEAH, ME TOO.
ESPECIALLY SAUSAGE.
ITALIAN SAUSAGE.
- [laughs]
- SORRY, I WAS GETTING INTO IT.
- ALL RIGHT.
WHAT SIZE ARE WE GOING WITH?
- HERE.
I WENT WITH THAT SIZE.
WOW. SORT OF FEELS LIKE
A PENIS.
NOW I WANT A PENIS.
- I WANT A PENIS FOR ONE DAY.
- ME TOO.
- JUST A DAY.
- WE'D DO DIRTY THINGS.
- I KNOW.
GONNA SLAP SOME PEOPLE
WITH IT--PEW, PEW!
- I WANNA KNOW HOW IT FEELS
TO, LIKE, DO IT.
- I'D GET KICKED IN THE NUTS
TO KNOW WHAT THAT FEELS LIKE.
- YEAH, ME TOO.
IT'S FLOPPY LIKE A PEE-PEE.
I'D LIKE TO PEE JUST TO SEE
IF I COULD, LIKE...
- WRITE MY NAME.
- WRITE MY NAME IN THE SNOW.
- DO YOU WANT 'EM LIKE THIS?
- EXACTLY LIKE THAT.
- WE DID GOOD.
- YOU DID VERY GOOD.
- AND I WANNA KNOW HOW IT FEELS
WHEN YOU GO RUNNING.
LIKE, DOES IT FLOP
BACK AND FORTH?
LIKE, WHERE DOES IT GO?
- YEAH, WHERE DO THE BALLS GO?
- TEAMWORK.
- [giggles] HI.
- HI.
- LOTS AND LOTS OF MEAT.
[crash]
OH, MY GOD!
YOUR FAT ASS BROKE IT!
- [laughing] OH, MY GOD!
- THAT'S SO RUDE.
SORRY.
- I SAT--[laughing]
- I DON'T KNOW HER.
- LORENZO.
SAY DADA.
- MA MA MA.
- DADA.
[Lorenzo babbling]
- HONEY, I'M HOME.
- HI!
- MAMA'S HERE!
- HI, DADA!
[Lorenzo shouts]
- AW!
- HI.
YOU'LL NEVER GUESS
WHAT WE JUST DID.
- WHAT?
- WE MADE PENISES!
- YOU MADE PENISES.
- YES.
WIENERS!
- [whistles]
- WE MADE THESE.
- LOOK AT THAT GUY!
YOU ACTUALLY DID THAT
FROM SCRATCH?
- YEAH.
- THAT'S PIG ASS.
- NOW YOU GUYS WANT ME
TO EAT THIS THAT YOU JUST DID?
- YOU'RE NOT GONNA EAT IT?
JIONNI, THAT'S SO RUDE.
WE BUSTED OUR ASSES
TO MAKE THESE SAUSAGE PEE-PEES.
SHE TRIED TO SLAP ME
IN THE FACE WITH IT.
- I ALWAYS WANTED TO HAVE
A PENIS FOR ONE--
[gasps]
- OH, MY GOD, STOP!
- I'M GONNA BREAK OUT NOW!
- * TELL ME YOUR NAME *
* I SWEAR I'LL DROP IT *
* WHENEVER I CAN *
- SALUTE.
- YEAH, SALUTE TO YOU TOO,
GUYS.
- TO OUR BARBECUE.
WHERE'S OUR FRIENDS?
- ALL FOUR OF THEM.
WHERE ARE THEY?
- WHO DO YOU THINK'S
GONNA SHOW UP FIRST?
I SAY SAM AND RON.
- I SAY SAM AND RON.
- SAM AND RON.
- * THE ROAD *
* THE ROAD IS LONG *
* THE ROAD *
* I'M ALWAYS SINGING *
- IT'S LIKE WE'RE MOVING IN.
- WELL, I LIKE TO BE
COMFORTABLE.
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE?
- THINK WE GOT IT.
[knock at door]
- OH!
- WE HAVE A GUEST.
IT'S DEENA.
- HI.
- [kisses]
- HI!
- HI, CHRIS. [kisses]
- WHAT'S UP?
- DEENA LOOKS GREAT,
CHRIS LOOKS GREAT,
AND I'M JUST EXCITED
TO CATCH UP
AND SEE WHAT THE HELL
THEY'VE BEEN DOING.
WHEN ARE YOU GUYS THINKING
ABOUT GETTING ENGAGED?
- YOU GUYS ARE ENGAGED?
- NO. NOT YET.
- THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT IT.
- LOOK AT HIM, HE'S TAPPING.
- YEAH, YOU GUYS ARE PUTTING ME
IN A TIGHT CORNER RIGHT NOW.
YEAH, WE FIGURE, GOTTA MOVE IN,
GET MARRIED,
THEN HAVE THE BABIES.
- WHAT ABOUT YOU GUYS?
- YEAH, WE'RE LOOKING...
- NEXT MONTH,
I'D LIKE TO START TRYING.
- TO GET A PLACE TOGETHER.
- OH, YEAH?
- WHAT'D YOU SAY?
- TRYING?
- OH, MY GOD!
- YOU SEE WHAT YOU'RE DOING
RIGHT THERE?
- I KNOW,
AND IT MIGHT TAKE A LONG TIME.
- YOU CAN'T SAY THAT
AND THEN NOT DO IT.
I'M GETTING SO EXCITED.
- IT MIGHT TAKE A LONG TIME.
- DID YOU GUYS THINK
OF BABY NAMES?
- I ACTUALLY WROTE DOWN--
- WHAT?
- WAIT A MINUTE--ARE YOU REALLY
DIGGING OUT A LIST RIGHT NOW?
- WOW!
- MELANI ALEXANDRA MATTHEWS?
- YEAH.
- SO WAIT A SECOND.
SHE DOESN'T HAVE SEX,
BUT SHE'S THINKING
ABOUT BABY NAMES.
- YOU GUYS ARE STILL
NOT HAVING SEX?
- NO, I'M HAVING SEX,
JUST A LOT WITH MYSELF.
- OH, IT SMELLS GOOD.
JIONNI'S BARBECUING.
AHH!
[knock at door]
- YES!
- IS THAT MY RONALD?
- WELCOME!
- OH.
- HEY, GUYS.
- HELLO.
HOW ARE YOU?
- WELCOME.
HI.
[kisses]
- WAIT, SHOW US AROUND.
- CHECK OUT THE BACK.
- YEAH.
- ON THE WATER.
- YOU LIVE
RIGHT ON THE WATER.
WOW, THIS IS NICE.
- THIS IS THE LIFE
RIGHT HERE.
- SEE THESE SAUSAGES?
- WHAT KIND ARE THESE?
- THEY WERE HAND-STUFFED.
- BY YOU?
- BY ME!
- BY JENNI AND NICOLE.
- ME AND JENNI DID IT.
RON, YOU'D BE IMPRESSED.
- YOU MIGHT WANT
THIS SIDE OF THE GRILL.
- JIONNI!
- I'LL TRY IT.
[laughs]
- IT'S SO NICE TO HAVE
THE GANG BACK TOGETHER
RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE HAVING
A BEAUTIFUL BARBECUE OUTSIDE,
AND IT JUST FEELS NICE.
SO...ENGAGEMENT?
- I THINK YOU'RE ASKING
THE WRONG PERSON.
[laughing]
- ENGAGEMENT?
- NO. NO RUSH.
- SHE WON'T PROPOSE TO ME.
I DON'T GET IT.
- [laughing]
I CALL [bleep] TO THAT.
I SAY TOMORROW IF RONNIE
POPPED THE QUESTION,
SAMMI WOULD SAY YES
WITHOUT A DOUBT.
- NICOLE, MAYBE NOW IS A GOOD
TIME TO TELL THEM WHAT YOU ARE.
- SO I WENT AND GOT
A DNA TEST.
- WHAT ARE YOU?
- I'M NOT EVEN CHILEAN
AT ALL.
- [gasps] GET OUT!
- REALLY?
- NO, WHAT'D THEY SAY?
- THEY SAID I WAS BORN IN CHILE,
BUT MY HERITAGE
IS SLOVAKIAN,
ROMANIAN,
GYPSY, RUSSIAN,
AND A LITTLE ASIAN.
- DON'T FORGET
THE JEWISH PART.
- "DON'T FORGET
THE JEWISH PART," HE GOES!
- NO, NOT LIKE
WHAT I BELIEVE IN,
LIKE, IT--LIKE, ISRAEL.
- YOU'RE JUST EVERYTHING.
- ISRAELIAN.
- GET YOUR YARMULKES ON.
I GOT CORNED BEEF
AND CABBAGE COMING.
- I WOULD HAVE BET
MY LIFE SAVINGS
THAT SHE IS
[bleep] 100% CHILEAN.
- ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
SOME OF THE FOOD'S OUT.
- YOU DON'T GOTTA
TELL ME TWICE.
- YEAH, LET'S DO IT.
- I'LL DO IT WITH YOU.
- BOW YOUR HEADS.
- EVERYBODY HOLDS HANDS.
- I THANK GOD FOR THIS FOOD
WE'RE ABOUT TO EAT,
FOR BRINGING
ALL OF OUR FRIENDS TOGETHER.
GOD BLESS EVERYONE
AND LORENZO
AND ALL OUR FAMILIES
AND FRIENDS.
AMEN.
all: AMEN.
- THAT WAS BEAUTIFUL.
- EXCELLENT.
- AS NICOLE WOULD SAY,
MAZEL TOV!
- JIONNI!
[laughter]
- YOU ALL GOT YARMULKES
UPSTAIRS--NOW, PUT 'EM ON.
- I'M WASTED RIGHT NOW.
- REALLY?
- WELL, DEE,
YOU'RE USED TO DRINKING,
I FEEL.
- WHOA, SOMEBODY'S HERE.
- HI, MA!
- HI.
- OH!
- MY MOM GETS HERE,
SO SHE CAN WATCH LORENZO.
- READY, GUYS?
- LET'S GO.
- BYE.
NOW IT'S TIME FOR US
TO GO TO THE BOARDWALK,
GO TO BEACHCOMBER,
AND GET SOME DRINKS.
- ARE WE TAKING A SHOT?
- CHOCOLATE PRETZEL SHOT?
- EIGHT CHOCOLATE PRETZELS.
- YOU WANT A CHOCOLATE PRETZEL?
NINE CHOCOLATE PRETZELS.
- NO, THERE'S EIGHT OF US.
- OH!
- WE GET TO THE BEACHCOMBER.
WE GOTTA DO A GROUP SHOT.
WE JUST CHEERS TO, YOU KNOW,
BEING TOGETHER
AND HAVING A GOOD NIGHT.
- I JUST TOLD SAM
HOW, LIKE, AWESOME IT IS
TO HAVE A CHILD.
- DID I TELL YOU
ABOUT HER FART?
- JIONNI!
- YEAH, THAT WAS FUNNY.
- I ALREADY TOLD YOU?
OKAY.
- IT COULD HAVE BEEN WORSE,
NICOLE, IT COULD HAVE--
- I COULD HAVE [bleep].
- YEP.
- DANNY'S GIRL--
SHE [bleep] EVERYWHERE,
LIKE, TWICE.
- THAT'S AWKWARD.
- HE TOLD ME.
- WAIT, HE TOLD YOU?
- HE SAW THE [bleep]?
- YEAH, HE SAW
EVERYTHING COME OUT.
- EW.
- HE WAS LIKE, "YEAH.
SHE [bleep] TWICE,
AND THEN THE BABY CAME OUT."
- LANDED IN THE [bleep],
OR...
- NO, THEY CLEAN
THE [bleep] UP.
- THEY PROBABLY GRAB IT.
- DO YOU WANT ANOTHER DRINK?
- I'M GOOD.
- I'LL GET ONE WITH YOU.
- ALL RIGHT. SAM?
- YOU GOOD?
- I'M GOOD RIGHT NOW, THANKS.
- YEAH, YOU'RE GOOD RIGHT NOW.
- I CAN'T DEAL HOW YOU GUYS
ARE STILL MUSHY
LIKE THE FIRST WEEK
YOU GUYS STARTED DATING.
- LATELY, IT'S BEEN--
KNOCK ON WOOD--
IT'S BEEN REALLY GOOD.
- I'M JUST SO HAPPY
THAT, YOU KNOW,
THEY MOVED IN TOGETHER,
THEY HARDLY FIGHT ANYMORE,
AND THEY'RE JUST LIKE
A GROWN COUPLE.
YOU DON'T WANT TO GET
ENGAGED SOON?
- I'M NOT IN A RUSH FOR IT.
I'M STILL, LIKE, SELFISH.
LIKE, I STILL WANT TO LIVE
MY LIFE FOR MYSELF, YOU KNOW?
- THAT'S WHAT JENNI SAID, BUT
NOW SHE WANTS TO START TRYING.
- TO HAVE KIDS?
I HOPE SO.
- I'VE BEEN BEGGING HER
TO HAVE A BABY.
SHE'S LIKE, "NO!
I LIKE TO GIVE THEM BACK."
BUT I KNOW IN HER HEAD
SHE REALLY WANTS A BABY.
- WE'RE BUILDING A HOUSE
ON MAIN.
- OH, REALLY?
- WE START THAT IN TWO WEEKS
AND MAKE BABIES
IN TWO WEEKS TOO.
- [laughs]
YEAH.
- I THINK WE'D BE, LIKE,
THE CUTEST PREGNANT LADIES.
- I'D BE A FAT [bleep].
- ME TOO!
- RIGHT, YEAH.
- I WOULDN'T EVEN BE A BITCH.
I WOULD BE A C-WORD.
- SO NOW YOU HEAR THAT,
AND NOW YOU THINK
I WANNA SIGN UP FOR THAT?
- WELL, I WOULD BE
A GREAT PREGNANT LADY.
- YOU'D BE TERRIBLE.
SHE'S MOODY NOW.
- LOOK, CAN YOU IMAGINE US
BEING TERRIBLE TOGETHER?
- NO, I'M NOT! REALLY?
- YOU'RE NOT MOODY?
I DON'T BELIEVE THAT DEE
WOULD MAKE A GOOD PREGNANT LADY.
I THINK SHE'LL BE MISERABLE
JUST LIKE ME.
- YEAH.
- YOU THINK I'LL BE MISERABLE
OR HAPPY?
- I KNOW YOU'LL BE MISERABLE.
- LIKE, HOW MISERABLE?
- LIKE, BEDRIDDEN,
"RUB MY FEET,
MY LEGS HURT..."
- DAMN RIGHT,
I DESERVE MY FEET RUBBED!
WANNA WALK THE BOARDWALK?
- YEAH.
I WANNA WALK THE BOARDWALK.
- LET'S GO.
- ALL RIGHT,
EVERYBODY READY?
GRAB YOUR GUNS, GUYS.
- WAIT, CHRIS--
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
ALL RIGHT, READY?
- YOU'RE TOAST.
- AT THE SOUND OF THE DING!
[bell dings]
WORK THAT THING!
AND WATCH 'EM GO,
WATCH 'EM RISE!
- FOR LORENZO, JIONNI.
- FIRST TO THE TOP
GETS YOUR PRIZE!
HERE WE GO,
IT'S AWFUL CLOSE!
[bell dings]
- YAY!
- WE GOT A WINNER.
- WHO WON?
WHO WON?
- NOT YOU.
- NINE. NINE IS THE WINNER.
GOOD SHOOTING.
- YAY, BABY!
- I ALMOST WON IT.
I THOUGHT I DID WIN.
BUT APPARENTLY, I DIDN'T.
- ALL RIGHT,
WHICH ONE YOU GONNA GET?
- CAN YOU PICK ONE
FOR LORENZO?
IT'S FOR MY SON!
THANKS, CHRIS!
- YOU'RE WELCOME.
- WHERE WE GOING, STEAKS?
- YEAH.
- * SHE'S JUST LIKE
EVERY GIRL *
- OBVIOUSLY, WE'RE GOING
TO STEAKS AFTER THE BOARDWALK,
BECAUSE THAT'S THE THING
TO DO.
YOU GET DRUNK, YOU PLAY GAMES,
THEN YOU GO TO STEAKS,
AND YOU PIG OUT.
- TWO SEASIDE TONYS
AND TWO CHEESE BALLS OVER HERE
FOR THE TWO FAT BOYS.
- I WANT CHEESE BALLS.
- I KINDA WANT A PIECE OF PIZZA.
- MAKE IT 3 CHEESE BALLS.
- 4 CHEESE BALLS.
- 5 CHEESE BALLS.
- 12 CHEESE BALLS!
- IT'S REALLY 5.
- AND A SLICE OF PIZZA,
PLEASE.
- I'M BEAT, MAN.
- NICOLE, THAT WAS, UH,
DEENA'S SLICE.
- STOP!
- WHY'D YOU JUST MAKE THAT FACE?
YOU JUST MADE
THE WORST FACE EVER.
- I DIDN'T EAT IT!
- AND SHE FINISHED IT!
SHE GOES,
"I DIDN'T EAT IT."
- SHE ATE THE WHOLE THING!
- IT WAS ME.
- STOP, JIONNI.
GUYS, IT WASN'T US.
- BABE, CAN YOU
POUR ME A WINE?
- OH, MY GOD!
- SHE'S BACK.
- DEENA, IS ONE
OF THESE CHEESE BALLS--
WE ORDERED,
LIKE, NINE ORDERS.
ROGER, DID YOU ORDER ONE?
- YEAH, I GOT ONE IN THERE
SOMEWHERE.
- DIDN'T I HAVE A PIZZA?
- IT'S RIGHT THERE.
- * GOT MY PIZZA *
I'M A BIG PIZZA PERSON.
[whispers]
I LOVE PIZZA.
WHO ATE MY PIZZA?
- OH, MY--
[laughter]
[laughing]
WHO THE [bleep] ATE MY PIZZA?
- YOU TOOK A BITE?
- I DON'T EVEN WANT
THIS [bleep] ANYMORE!
[laughter]
- THERE'S MORE
SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW ON THE WAY...
- AND IT CONTINUES NOW.
- WAIT, WHERE DID
MY WINEGLASS GO?
- ARE YOU GUYS
GONNA DO IT?
- NO.
- IT'S GETTING AWKWARD
IN HERE.
- IF YOU ASKED ME
TO DRAW YOU A SKETCH
OF JENNI'S VAGINA RIGHT NOW,
I COULDN'T DO IT.
- JENNI, I'M SO SICK OF HIM
TALKING ABOUT IT.
JUST DO SOMETHING
FOR THE GUY.
- MADE YOU
A WHOLE FRENCH DINNER,
AND I GOT A POUND FOR IT.
- ME AND ROGER WENT ALL OUT
MAKING THIS FRENCH MEAL.
- BABE, YOU'RE NOT VERY NICE.
- NICOLE CRIED.
HUGGED ME WITH TEARS.
[laughing] JENNI GOES,
"WHAT'S UP, BRO?"
- I DID NOT.
- [laughing]
- YOU GUYS ARE MEANT
FOR EACH OTHER.
YOU'RE LIKE THE SAME...
- NO, I'M HAPPY
WITH THE BITCH I'VE GOT.
SHE WANTS ME TO BE...
SHE WANTS ME TO BE
MR. ROMANTIC.
SHE WANTS ME TO BE,
OH, YOU GOTTA CHANGE YOUR WAYS,
YOU GOTTA, YOU KNOW, BE MORE
ROMANTIC, WINE ME, DINE ME.
I MAKE HER A DINNER,
SHE'S LIKE, "'SUP, DUDE?"
SERIOUSLY.
- YOU WANNA GO UPSTAIRS?
- [clears throat]
SO ENJOY OUR SHORE HOUSE,
FOLKS,
BUT IT'S TIME FOR US
TO GO TO BED.
- EW.
- SO YOU WANNA GET IN
BEFORE LORENZO WAKES UP.
- I'M NOT READY
TO GO TO BED YET.
I WANT TO SIT OUTSIDE
AND JUST DRINK THE WINE.
- GOOD NIGHT.
- WE MIGHT BE SHORT,
BUT WE LOVE EACH OTHER.
[laughter]
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, I WILL
SEE YOU IN THE MANANA.
I'M GOING TO SLEEP.
- GOOD NIGHT.
- I WANNA SIT RIGHT HERE.
- DEENA, YOU GOT BIRD [bleep]
RIGHT THERE
ALL OVER YOUR THIGH.
- IT'S ON ME?
- OH! AH!
DEENA JUST SAT
IN BIRD [bleep].
- [laughing]
- I'M GONNA GET MORE WINE.
- SHE MIGHT FALL ASLEEP.
- I KNOW.
- OH!
[gasps]
COOL.
ALL RIGHT, I GET IT.
I [bleep].
BIG MESS.
- WHAT IS SHE DOING NOW?
- I CAN'T SEE.
- OH, MY GOD!
- OH, MY GOD.
- WHAT SHOULD I DO?
- HOW'D YOU DO THAT?
- I, LIKE, WAS WALKING,
AND I TRIPPED.
- WHAT DID YOU TRIP ON?
- MYSELF.
- HER FEET.
- THAT'S TYPICAL.
- I'M SURPRISED
SHE DIDN'T FALL.
- THAT'S TERRIBLE, THAT'S BAD.
- I KNOW IT IS.
- I DON'T EVEN KNOW
HOW TO GET IT OUT.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
CAN I HAVE MY WINE?
- IT'S ON THE COUCH.
[laughter]
- AFTER YOU SPILLED,
DID YOU REFILL?
- I DID.
- OH, MY GOD.
OH, YOU'RE FUNNY.
I CAN'T TAKE YOU.
- YOU'RE SUCH [bleep].
I HATE YOU ALL.
- * CLOSE YOUR *
* YOUR E-E-EYES *
[Lorenzo sneezes]
- BLESS YOU.
- OH, BLESS YOU, MY LOVE.
- WHO IS THAT?
- HI, DADA!
- OH!
- HEY.
- WOW, LOOK AT THIS THING.
- GOOD MORNING!
- THIS THING'S SICK.
SMELLS WEIRD IN HERE.
- YEAH.
- LIKE WHAT?
- SMELLS LIKE...
- WINE.
- IT'S PROBABLY DEENA.
- SHE SPILLED WINE
ALL OVER THE COUCH.
- WHERE?
- THE OTHER ONE.
- OTHER COUCH.
THAT ONE.
- LOOK HOW BAD IT IS.
- OH, [bleep].
- IT FADED.
BU LAST NIGHT IT WAS BAD.
- JIONNI, CALL DEENA.
- CALL HER?
- YEAH.
LET'S PRETEND WE'RE MAD
ABOUT THE CUSHION.
[line ringing]
- MM! WHAT'S THIS?
- HELLO?
- DEENA?
- WHO'S THAT?
- HI.
- MY COUCH IS RUINED!
- I'M SORRY
ABOUT YOUR CUSHION.
- SON OF A GUN, YOU.
- I'M GONNA PAY FOR IT.
I TRIPPED
OVER MY [bleep] SANDAL.
- I'M GONNA LOSE THE DEPOSIT
ON THIS HOUSE NOW
SINCE YOU STAINED MY COUCH.
- I'M SORRY.
- I WON'T GET MY MONEY BACK,
AND LORENZO
CAN'T GO TO COLLEGE NOW.
- WELL...
REALLY?
OKAY.
- CHRIS IS GETTING A BEATING.
- RELAX.
I'LL PAY
FOR THE [bleep] COUCH.
- WELL, I WISH I GOT
TO SAY GOOD-BYE.
WE LITERALLY WOKE UP, LIKE,
TEN MINUTES AFTER YOU LEFT.
- OH, I'M SORRY.
YEAH, WE HAD TO GO.
CHRIS HAS WORK,
AND I HAVE TO BE IN THE CITY.
- I'M REALLY NOT UPSET
ABOUT THE COUCH.
I MEAN, IT'S A SHORE HOUSE.
[bleep] HAPPENS.
YOU KNOW, IT'S DEENA.
SHE DOES [bleep] LIKE THIS
ALL THE TIME.
- YOU SHOULD HAVE HEARD
DEENA AND CHRIS
WERE LIKE AN OLD MARRIED COUPLE
LAST NIGHT.
JENNI HAD THE KID'S NAME
PICKED OUT LAST NIGHT.
- SHE HAS THE WEDDING,
THE ENGAGEMENT PARTY,
THE HONEYMOON, AND HIS FUNERAL
ALREADY PLANNED OUT.
- SHE SAID THAT SHE SENDS HIM
RINGS ALL THE TIME.
- REALLY?
- THAT'S CREEPY.
- I DON'T EVEN DO THAT.
- YEAH.
- I THINK.
- I'D HAVE TO CHANGE
MY NUMBER!
[laughing]
- WAS IT HER OR SOMEONE ELSE?
- OH, GOOD JOB.
LOOK AT THAT.
- YAY!
- GOOD JOB.
PUT IT RIGHT IN MY COFFEE,
BUDDY--NICE!
YOU'RE GONNA BE KILLING
THOSE BOARDWALK GAMES LATER.
- IT WAS SO FUN TO HAVE
THE OLD ROOMIES OVER.
WE HAD A GREAT TIME.
- WE DID A GREAT JOB HOSTING.
- MM-HMM.
- YOU READY?
- YEAH.
- GIVE ME A HUG GOOD-BYE.
COME HERE.
OOH!
- RONNIE AND SAM
ARE AWESOME WITH LORENZO,
AND I HONESTLY WOULD
TRUST THEM TO BABYSIT.
- HE'S COMING HOME WITH ME.
- NO, HE'S NOT.
- UH, WE'RE TAKING THE BABY.
AND WE'RE TAKING THE BABY,
BY THE WAY.
- THEY WOULD BE
A-MAZING PARENTS.
BYE.
SAY BYE.
- I'M GONNA TRY TO
WASH THIS OUTSIDE--IT STINKS.
- I WANNA TAKE HIM HOME
WITH ME.
- GREAT TO SEE
MY OLD FRIENDS.
ROOMMATE NIGHT
WAS DEFINITELY A SUCCESS.
- YES, WE HAD AN AMAZING TIME,
AND I'M SO GLAD WE DECIDED
TO DO THE COUPLES NIGHT,
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE
THAT'S JUST HOW WE DO IT NOW.
- COUPLES.
- MM-HMM.
SHOULD I GET DETERGENT?
- YEAH.
- LET ME DO IT.
JIONNI, LET ME DO SOMETHING-AH!
PAIN IN MY [bleep].
- SOMETHING-AH.
PAIN IN YOUR [bleep]?
[Nicole laughs]
- HOLD ON, HOLD ON, HOLD ON.
WATER FIRST.
ALL RIGHT, HEADS UP.
- JIONNI!
OH, MY GOD!
JIONNI.
YOU DON'T WANNA GET IT
SOAKED LIKE THAT.
- LET IT GO.
OH!
- KARMA'S A BITCH.
- JUST GOT STUNG IN THE NECK!
[laughter]
- OH, MY GOD, YOU DID.
- IT'S NOT SO MUCH RIGHT HERE...
- JESUS!
both: RIGHT HERE!
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT STUNG ME.
GOT ME RIGHT IN THE NECK.
- JESUS.
- REALLY?
- [laughing] OH, MY GOD!
- JIONNI, IT'S BAD.
GOD PUNCHED YOU
FOR BEING RUDE TO ME.
- YEAH, YOU'RE PROBABLY
DYING RIGHT NOW.
A SLOW DEATH.
- OH, MY GOD, STOP!
- I DID NOT INHALE,
AND I DID NOT HAVE SEX
WITH THAT GIRL.
- YES, YOU DID!
[both laughing]
[horns honking]
- OH, MY--
CAN I HAVE MY MONEY BACK?
TWO...THREE.
all: HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
[cheers and applause]