- BABY, YOU ALL RIGHT
IN THERE?
OF COURSE I'M GONNA DO
WHAT I DO,
AND I'M GONNA JUMP OUT
AND SCARE THE CRAP OUT OF HER
LIKE THIS CRAZED GORILLA
THAT I AM.
BAAHH!
[laughs]
- OW! OW.
[both laughing]
- [laughing]
YOU ALMOST JUST WENT--
[laughs]
- OH, MY GOD.
- [laughing] I'M SORRY.
- WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
[Icona Pop's I Love It]
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* *
* I DON'T CARE *
- OW!
EXCUSE ME.
[gasps]
OH, MY GOD!
LORENZO, THAT HURT.
CAN WE CUDDLE?
[baby babbling and crying]
WHY DON'T YOU LIKE ME?
EVERY TIME I HOLD LORENZO
HE STARTS CRYING.
THAT'S SO RUDE.
LIKE, I GAVE BIRTH TO YOU.
WHY DON'T YOU LIKE ME?
[phone ringing]
- HELLO?
- HI, JANIS.
- HOW'S IT GOING?
- GOOD, WE'RE JUST
GETTING USED TO BEING ALONE.
- HOW'S YOUR LITTLE BABY?
- HE'S GOOD.
HE LOVES IT HERE.
I FEEL LIKE HE'S HAPPY.
BUT HE STILL LIKES
JIONNI MORE.
- NO, HE DOESN'T.
- YEAH, HE DOES.
EVERY TIME I GO AND TRY
AND, LIKE, HOLD HIM,
HE STARTS CRYING
AND HE WANTS JIONNI.
- THAT'S BECAUSE JIONNI DOES ALL
THAT ROUGHNECK STUFF WITH HIM.
YOU JUST HAVE TO DO
THE SAME KIND OF THING.
LIKE THAT MOMMY DATE THING
THAT THEY DO.
- WELL, I KNOW THERE'S
"MOMMY AND ME" SWIM CLASSES
THAT I HEARD ABOUT.
- YEAH, THAT'S GREAT.
- I JUST WANT HIM TO LIKE ME.
- HE LOVES YOU.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
- MM, NO, HE DOESN'T.
- HE LOVES YOU, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
ALL RIGHT,
I'LL SEE YOU GUYS SOON NOW.
- OKAY, WE MISS YOU.
- TALK TO YOU LATER.
- LOVE YOU, BYE.
ALL RIGHT, I'M LEAVING.
[singing]
WE'RE GONNA GO SEE BOO BOO.
WE'RE GONNA GO SEE JENNY.
WE'RE HERE, LORENZO.
HI! AND THEY'RE NOT BARKING.
- WHERE'S THE DOGS?
THAT'S WEIRD.
- TOLD YOU.
- IT WORKS?
- NO, I DON'T WANT TO JINX IT.
OKAY, DO YOU WANT TO GO
OUT THERE?
- YEAH.
NOELL!
YOU SEE NOELL?
- UGH!
- THIS IS BEAUTIFUL BACK HERE.
SO WE'RE GOING
TO SWIM LESSONS TODAY.
- YOU GONNA GET ALL THE GIRLS?
- NO.
- [laughs]
- NO GIRLS.
- PBBT.
- YEAH.
- I DON'T THINK SO.
YOU'RE MY BABY.
YOU'RE GONNA STAY THAT WAY.
YOU'RE NEVER GONNA HAVE SEX,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA TOUCH
ANYBODY'S BOOBS,
AND YOU'RE GONNA STAY HOME
IN MOMMY'S BASEMENT FOREVER.
JUST LIKE JIONNI.
HIGH FIVE.
GO AHEAD.
YEAH!
- [laughs]
- HI, ARE YOU HERE FOR SWIMMING?
- YES,
THE "MOMMY AND ME" SWIM CLASS.
- OH, GOOD, YEAH.
- I REALLY HOPE THAT LORENZO
ENJOYS THIS CLASS.
I FEEL LIKE IT'LL STRENGTHEN
OUR BOND A LITTLE BIT.
I ALREADY LOVE HIM TO DEATH.
I JUST WANT HIM TO LOVE ME BACK.
- SO WE'LL DO EACH ONE'S NAME,
AND THEN,
WHEN IT'S YOUR CHILD'S NAME,
YOU'LL LIFT THEM UP.
WHERE IS LORENZO?
- LORENZO--
OH, WHOOPS.
- WHERE IS LORENZO? [laughs]
- IS HE SMILING?
- THEY'RE SWIMMING IN THE WATER.
UP AND DOWN.
A LITTLE BIT.
- SPLASH, SPLASH.
- COOL.
- THAT'S A BABY.
- ISN'T SHE PRETTY?
- ANGELINA.
- HI.
- HELLO.
- WHO IS THAT?
[laughter]
- SHE'S GOT BIG EYES.
- HE'S SO HANDSOME, ISN'T HE?
- YOU FLIRTING?
- I FEEL LIKE LORENZO'S
A LADIES' MAN, AND I FEEL LIKE
WHEN HE SEES OTHER CUTE BABIES,
ESPECIALLY GIRLS,
YOU KNOW, HE JUST WANTS
TO GET THEIR NUMBER.
- YEAH!
- LORENZO!
- [laughs]
DON'T SPLASH MOMMY.
[baby babbling]
- OH. [laughs]
- ALL RIGHT.
I WISH I DIDN'T WEAR EYELASHES
AND MAKEUP TO THIS CLASS,
BUT LORENZO'S HAVING
A GOOD TIME.
HE'S SMILING, HE'S KICKING.
THIS IS WHAT I WANTED.
YOU'RE SUCH A LADIES' MAN.
I CAN'T TAKE IT.
IT'S MORNING.
I'M GONNA GO DO INTERVIEWS
TO FIND HIM A BABYSITTER.
- OKAY.
- I WANT, LIKE, AN OLD LADY.
- OLD LADY?
- I'M GONNA FIND YOU
A BABYSITTER!
NOT HAVING JANIS AROUND
IS DEFINITELY GONNA SUCK,
BECAUSE IF WE WANT TO GO OUT ON
A DOUBLE DATE OR GO SOMEWHERE,
WE NEED SOMEBODY
TO WATCH LORENZO.
IT'S A LITTLE SCARY TO US,
BECAUSE WE'RE USED TO HAVING
FAMILY WATCH LORENZO.
- YEAH, WE HAVEN'T
DONE THAT YET.
WE HAVE TO FIND SOMEBODY
PROFESSIONAL.
- PROFESSIONAL, DEFINITELY.
JESUS.
- WOW, YOU LOOK NICE.
- DID HE EAT?
- YUP.
- COME TO MAMA.
[baby babbling]
COME.
- OH, MY GOD!
- [screams]
HE TOOK A STEP!
OH, MY GOD. [laughs]
- HE'S GONNA WALK THIS SUMMER.
- I'M GONNA CRY.
I JUST WANT HIM TO BE
MY BABY FOREVER,
BUT I KNOW IT'S INEVITABLE,
HE'S GONNA HOOK UP WITH GIRLS,
HE'S GONNA HAVE GIRLFRIEND--
- SLOBBER KNOBBERS.
- STOP!
- [laughs]
- [scoffs] I JUST DON'T WANT
TO THINK ABOUT LORENZO
HOOKING UP WITH GIRLS!
- HOOK-UPS, KARMA.
- HE'S ONE YEARS OLD,
YOU PERVERT!
- [laughs]
YOU'RE REALLY GONNA CRY?
- STOP. STOP IT.
- OH!
- LET'S CALL AUNT BOO BOO.
[phone ringing]
- HELLO?
- MORNING, BOO.
- MORNING.
SO REMEMBER HOW I TOLD YOU
I WANTED TO GO FIND BABYSITTERS?
- YEAH.
- WELL, I FOUND A FEW.
I WAS GONNA GO
INTERVIEW THEM TODAY
AT, LIKE, A CAFE,
OR SOMETHING,
AND I WANTED YOU
TO COME WITH ME.
YOU KNOW,
JUST WEED OUT THE CRAZIES.
- AWESOME. YAY.
- I WANT TO DO IT
AT A RESTAURANT,
AND NOT AT MY HOUSE,
BECAUSE IF I DON'T PICK PEOPLE,
AND THEY GET MAD
AND EGG MY HOUSE,
I DON'T NEED THAT [bleep].
- STALKERS.
- YEAH.
- GIVE THE BABY A KISS FOR ME.
- OKAY, I LOVE YOU, BYE.
- LOVE YOU.
- IF I CAN'T FIND A BABYSITTER,
THEN THAT MEANS
THAT WE CAN'T DO DOUBLE DATES,
AND--
- JANIS IS GONNA HAVE TO
MOVE IN.
OH, MY GOD.
TALKED TO NICOLE.
WE'RE GONNA GO
LOOK FOR BABYSITTERS,
SO THEY CAN ENJOY
THEIR SUMMER IN SEASIDE
AND LIKE,
GET OUT WITH US.
- LET'S DO SOMETHING FUN
WITH THEM.
- YEAH.
- I FEEL LIKE WE DO DINNER
ALL THE TIME,
LET'S DO SOMETHING--
- I KNOW.
BUT I DON'T HAVE ANY IDEAS.
I WANT, LIKE, CRAZY.
- IT'S JUST IMPORTANT
TO SWITCH IT UP,
KEEP THINGS INTERESTING.
- WE WANT TO DO SOMETHING
ADVENTUROUS.
LIKE, I TOOK NICOLE--WHEN
WE WERE LIVING IN JERSEY CITY,
I TOOK HER TO THIS PLACE
CALLED "NINJA"...
- MM-HMM.
- AND NINJAS JUMPED OUT
AND SCARED
THE BEJESUS OUT OF HER.
- YEAH, I FEEL LIKE
SHE SCARES REALLY EASY.
- YEAH, BUT IT'S FUN.
- THERE'S THIS PLACE
IN PHILLY,
IT'S--IT'S LIKE AN ASYLUM.
IT'S LIKE A CLOSED-DOWN PRISON
FROM--I THINK IT'S,
LIKE, THE 1800s.
AND IT'S HAUNTED.
I USED TO TAKE GIRLS THERE
BACK IN THE DAY
AND GET 'EM ALL SCARED,
AND THEN I'D BRING 'EM HOME,
AND THEY'D JUST WANT
TO SNUGGLE UP NEXT TO ME.
- SERIOUSLY?
SERIOUS--YOU'RE SERIOUS,
AREN'T YOU?
- [laughs]
- YOU ARE.
SO YOU'RE TAKING ME
WHERE YOU BROUGHT ANOTHER BITCH?
- YOU PICK IT.
HOW 'BOUT THAT?
- NO, I DON'T MIND.
- OH, OKAY.
- I'M HOTTER ANYWAYS.
- MM, THAT'S TRUE, ACTUALLY.
- OH, I KNOW IT IS.
- HEY, BOO.
YOU LOOK PRETTY.
- SO DO YOU.
- IF I HAVE TO GET A BABYSITTER,
AND I'M GONNA INTERVIEW PEOPLE,
I JUST WANT TO KNOW FIRSTHAND,
DO YOU HAVE A CRIMINAL RECORD?
DO YOU DO DRUGS?
ARE YOU A CHILD MOLESTER?
I WANT TO KNOW IT ALL, BECAUSE,
YOU KNOW, THIS IS MY BABY,
AND NOBODY'S GONNA
[bleep] WITH HIM.
I DIDN'T SLEEP ALL NIGHT.
IT'S LIKE A STRANGER
WATCHING MY KID.
LIKE, IT'S A BIG DEAL.
- [gasps] HEY.
- OH, HI.
- HI.
- HI! GRANDMA'S HERE.
EVERYTHING'S COOL.
OH, MY GOD,
YOU'RE SO COOL ALREADY.
- OH, THANK YOU.
- SO DO YOU WANT TO, LIKE,
TELL US ABOUT YOURSELF
BEFORE WE START GRILLING YOU?
- I'M A SENIOR CITIZEN.
I LOVE CHILDREN.
I LOVE BABIES.
THEY'RE SO CUTE.
- HOW ARE YOU YOU?
- STARTED OUT
AS A FUNERAL DIRECTOR/EMBALMER.
I LIVED IN A FUNERAL HOME
SINCE I WAS BORN.
- YOU EMBALMED BODIES?
- YEAH, YEAH.
- OH, MY GOD!
VERY CREEPY,
THE FACT THAT JODINA
WAS BORN AND RAISED
IN A FUNERAL HOME.
LIKE, DEAD BODIES?
- YES, DEAD ONES.
- SOME PEOPLE HAVE TO
LIVE THEIR LIVES LIKE THAT.
LIKE, THAT'S THEIR JOB.
IF IT WASN'T FOR THEM--
- AND THAT'S CREEPY.
I HAVE A LOT OF QUESTIONS
FOR YOU.
- OKAY.
- DO YOU BELIEVE IN GHOSTS?
- YES.
- ME TOO.
HOW DO YOUR BOOBS LOOK?
- DOWN TO MY BELLY BUTTON.
- MINE ARE ALREADY THERE.
- [laughs]
- WOULD YOU CHANGE YOUR DIAPER
BEFORE OR AFTER LORENZO'S?
- OH, HE WOULD COME FIRST.
- OKAY.
- DO YOU HAVE SEX?
- YES!
- WITH WHO?
- STOP.
- A MAN.
- OH.
- DO YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS
FOR HER?
- NOT ANYMORE.
- ALL RIGHT.
- YOU LOOK STONED.
- I'M NOT. I WISH I WAS, THOUGH.
- YOU KNOW THIS IS AN INTERVIEW
TO BE A BABYSITTER TO MY SON?
- YEAH, I KNOW.
I KNOW.
COULD I GET A BEER?
- IT'S NOT EVEN 12:00.
- THAT'S SO SOMETHING YOU WOULD
DO BEFORE YOU HAD LORENZO.
- EXACTLY, BUT I WOULD NEVER GO
TO A BABYSITTING INTERVIEW.
- AND YOU WOULD NEVER GET HIRED.
- NO.
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
- [laughs]
- WOULD YOU CONSIDER YOURSELF
A COUGAR?
- YOU THINK SO?
YOU LIKE MY LEOPARD HERE?
- YEAH.
- I LIKE THE LEOPARD.
- SO IF JIONNI WAS HOME,
WOULD YOU, LIKE,
TRY AND GET WITH HIM?
- JIONNI? NO, ME?
- JUST WONDERING.
YOU KNOW, THAT JUST
MAKES ME FEEL BETTER.
LIKE, THAT'S MY MAN,
[bleep].
- I'M HAVING, LIKE,
AN EPIPHANY RIGHT NOW.
- YEAH. [laughs]
- I FEEL LIKE YOU'RE GONNA BE
ME WHEN I'M OLDER. [laughs]
- YEAH, YOU'RE US.
- I'M KENNY.
YEAH, HOW YOU DOING?
- HOW YOU DOING?
NICE TO MEET YOU.
- HE USED TO WORK AT KARMA.
- OH, REALLY?
- OH, YEAH, YEAH.
- YEAH.
- YOU AND I ALMOST
ACTUALLY HAD A MOMENT.
- YOU ACTUALLY DID.
- STOP.
- [laughs] I SWEAR TO--
- SWEAR TO GOD.
- COME ON!
- WE DID, WE DID.
[both laughing]
- DO YOU REMEMBER YOU BACK THEN?
YOU WOULD'VE MADE OUT
WITH A TRAY.
- I KNOW, I WAS SICK.
- YOU WERE.
- SICK INDIVIDUAL.
- UGH.
- HE USED TO BE AT THE BACK BAR
BY THE WOMEN'S BATHROOM.
IT WAS THE BAR
WE ALWAYS WENT TO!
- BECAUSE I REMEMBER
EVERY TIME I WENT TO KARMA.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
I WAS A [bleep].
I WOULD'VE SLEPT
WITH ANYTHING THAT WALKED.
- [laughs] YOU DID
SLEEP WITH ANYTHING THAT WALKED.
[both laughing]
- STOP.
MY PAST IS COMING TO HAUNT ME.
- THIS INTERVIEWING [bleep]
IS HARDER THAN I--
- YEAH, IT'S STRESSFUL.
- THERE'S GOTTA BE DECENT PEOPLE
OUT THERE, THOUGH.
- YEAH, THERE'S GOTTA
BE NORMAL PEOPLE OUT THERE
THAT KNOW WHAT THE [bleep]
THEY'RE DOING.
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
GOTTA WORK WITH IT.
[footsteps approaching]
- HI, HOW ARE YOU?
- HELLO.
- I'M MADISON.
- JENNY.
- OH, YOU'RE SO CUTE.
- I'M MADISON.
- HI.
HERE'S MY RESUME.
- OH, COOL.
ALL RIGHT, THANK YOU.
MADISON WALKS IN, AND
I JUST NOTICE HOW PRETTY SHE IS.
SHE LOOKS SO CLASSY
AND SHE LOOKS PROFESSIONAL,
SO I FEEL LIKE, YOU KNOW,
I HAVE HOPE WITH THIS GIRL.
SO DO YOU DRINK A LOT
OR DO DRUGS?
- ABSOLUTELY NOT.
- DO YOU GO TO KARMA AT ALL?
- NO.
- BAMBOO?
- NO CLUBS?
- NO.
IT'S NOT REALLY MY SCENE.
- UM, SO DO YOU HAVE
ANY EXPERIENCE BABYSITTING?
- YES, I HAVE
A FIVE-YEAR-OLD BROTHER
AND I HAVE
AN EIGHT-YEAR-OLD SISTER.
I ALSO WORK
AT COLOR ME MINE POTTERY STUDIO.
I DO ALL THE CHILDREN'S
BIRTHDAY PARTIES.
I'M THE MANAGER THERE,
SO I LIKE TO GO IN EARLY,
GET THE PARTY SET UP.
- JUST BY YOURSELF?
- YEAH.
- WOW.
THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S CRAZY.
I'M SO IMPRESSED.
DO YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS?
- WILL YOU STILL BE BABYSITTING
IN A FEW YEARS?
- ABSOLUTELY.
- I MEAN, THIS GIRL
IS LIKE AN ANGEL.
I THINK YOU'RE THE BEST ONE,
SO...
- THANK YOU, PERFECT.
- I SAY YOU'RE HIRED.
- THANK YOU,
THAT'S WONDERFUL.
- RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- THIS GIRL'S PERFECT.
- SHE'S A GOOD KID.
- I JUST HOPE JIONNI
DOESN'T LOOK AT HER BOOBS.
- WHAT?
- SHE'S [bleep] AWESOME.
- THAT WAS LIKE ME.
- LIKE, THAT'S LIKE I SAY.
THAT'S, LIKE, A GOOD GIRL.
- THAT WAS ME.
I WAS GOOD ONCE.
- YOU WERE THAT SWEET?
- YES.
- I CAN'T EVEN.
[bleep] HAPPENED TO YOU,
JUICE HEADS?
- LONG ISLAND HAPPENED TO ME,
AND THEN THE SHORE, OKAY?
- SHOULD'VE STAYED UPSTATE.
- NO, I WOULD BE FAT
WITH SIX KIDS.
- I SHOULD'VE STAYED
OFF MYSPACE.
[both laughing]
SO NOW WE HAVE A BABYSITTER,
AND WE CAN GO OUT,
AND WE CAN DO OUR THING.
- GOOD, 'CAUSE I WANT
TO PLAN SOMETHING SOON.
LIKE NOW.
WE SHOULD'VE SEEN IF SHE WAS
AVAILABLE IN A COUPLE HOURS.
- FOR REAL?
- YEAH,
I WANT TO TAKE YOU OUT TONIGHT.
- I'M SO EXCITED.
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
- I HAVE A SPOT
ME AND ROGER PICKED.
A LITTLE FAR AWAY, BUT...
- OKAY.
- JUST WEAR COMFY CLOTHES.
- I HATE SURPRISES.
- YOU SHOULD LOVE SURPRISES.
- NO, I LIKE TO KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON.
- WHY?
- I DON'T LIKE IT.
[burps]
- YOU BE GOOD
FOR BABYSITTER MADISON?
- NO SPITTING.
- HORSEPLAY.
- NO HORSEPLAY.
- DON'T PULL HER HAIR.
- YOU CAN PULL HER HAIR.
- NO, DON'T PULL HER HAIR.
- YOU CAN PULL
A LITTLE BIT OF HAIR.
- NO.
- 'ELLO?
- HI.
[knocking at the door]
- COME IN.
WHAT ARE YOU WEARING?
- I ONLY HAD TWO PAIRS OF BOOTS
WITH ME, SO...
- OH, MY GOD, YOU GUYS BOTH
BUY EXACT SAME JEANS.
SHE HAD THOSE JEANS ON
YESTERDAY.
- JENNY'S NOT WEARING HEELS AND
WE'RE GOING ON A DOUBLE DATE.
WE HAVE TO BE DOING
SOMETHING WEIRD.
LIKE, IT'S NOT JUST A DATE.
- SOMETHING--
SOMETHING'S DIFFERENT.
- YEAH.
- JIONNI, GET THE DOOR.
- JIONNI, GET THE DOOR,
I THINK
IT'S THE BABYSITTER.
- HI.
- HI, JIONNI, HOW ARE YOU?
I'M MADISON, NICE TO MEET YOU.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
- THANKS FOR COMING
ON SUCH SHORT NOTICE.
THIS IS LORENZO.
- HI! YOU'RE SO ADORABLE.
- THANKS.
WE LEFT YOU A LIST.
WE'VE NEVER DONE THIS BEFORE,
SO--[scoffs]
WE JUST WROTE
OUR CELL PHONE NUMBERS.
- OKAY.
- HIS FOOD--HIS SNACKS
AND PUFFS, THEY'RE ALL THERE.
- OKAY.
- IT'S DEFINITELY HARD TO LEAVE
LORENZO WITH A STRANGER.
WE'RE NOT USED TO THAT, WE'RE
USED TO FAMILY WATCHING LORENZO,
SO THIS IS, LIKE,
A BIG STEP FOR US.
- I'M DEFINITELY
THINKING ABOUT IT.
- IT'S HARD.
- IT'S IN THE BACK OF MY MIND.
- LOVE YOU.
- BYE, DADA.
- SAY "BYE, MOMMY.
BYE, DADDY."
- ALL RIGHT, KIDS, I'M READY.
- BYE, GUYS.
- YOU WANT THIS BALL?
THERE YOU GO.
- YOU DRIVING?
- ROGER IS.
ENZO'S CAFE ITALIA.
- ENZO?
- MM-HMM.
- [gasps]
IT'S LORENZO'S PLACE.
I WONDER HOW HE'S DOING.
- WHY DON'T YOU CALL HER?
- GIVE HER A FEW MINUTES.
HER BOYFRIEND PROBABLY
JUST GOT THERE.
- UGH, PLEASE.
[phone ringing]
- [gasps]
LORENZO,
I THINK MOM'S CALLING.
- HI.
- HI, MOLLY.
- HEY, HOW ARE THEY DOING?
- GOOD, HE JUST WOKE UP.
HE'S PLAYING.
DO YOU WANT TO SAY HI?
- YEAH.
- SAY HI TO MOMMY.
- HI, LORENZO.
- SAY HI.
- IT'S DADA.
- HE SAYS HI.
HE'S SMILING.
- ALL RIGHT, COOL.
- THANKS AGAIN.
- THANK YOU.
SAY "BYE, MOMMY."
- BYE, LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU.
- ARE YOU KIDS EXCITED?
- WHERE ARE WE GOING?
- NERVOUS?
- I DON'T LIKE SURPRISES.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT WE'RE DOING.
- ARE YOU CLAUSTROPHOBIC?
- VERY.
- YOU MAY NOT LIVE
TO MAKE IT BACK.
- IS THIS LIFE-THREATENING?
- YES, I'M GONNA BE HONEST
WITH YOU.
IT'S POTENTIALLY--WE'RE GONNA
MAKE IT AS SAFE AS IT CAN BE,
BUT IT'S POTENTIALLY
LIFE-THREATENING.
- WHERE THE [bleep]
ARE WE GOING?
YOU KILLING US?
- NO.
NOT YET.
- NOT YET?
- NOT YET.
- IS THERE A BATHROOM HERE?
- [bleep] IS THIS?
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
- THIS IS NOT
A ROMANTIC DOUBLE DATE.
- ALL RIGHT, KIDS.
- WE'RE HERE.
- UGH,
I DON'T FEEL SO GOOD.
- [spooky humming]
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- THIS IS A [bleep]
HAUNTED HOUSE!
- IS THAT WHY
YOU'RE GONNA THROW UP?
- KIND OF.
OH, I GOTTA POOP.
[laughter]
- WELCOME.
- I FEEL LIKE
I'M GONNA [bleep] MY PANTS
AND THROW UP
AT THE SAME TIME.
I MEAN, I DON'T FEEL GOOD
RIGHT NOW,
AND I FEEL LIKE
THAT'S CALLED ANXIETY.
- HEY, GUYS.
- OH!
- [laughing] WHAT'S UP?
- WELCOME TO PENNHURST.
I'LL BE YOUR PARANORMAL
INVESTIGATOR TONIGHT.
- OH, MY [bleep]!
- SHE'S GONNA BE
YOUR PSYCHIC MEDIUM.
- I WANT TO BE SCARED, I WANT
TO LEAVE HERE TERRIFIED, AND--
- I WANT A GHOST TO PUNCH ME
IN THE [bleep] FACE.
- I DO TOO. I WOULD--
- I WANT BRUISES ALL OVER.
- OH, YEAH.
I WOULD LOVE TO SEE THAT.
- SHUT UP!
- WHAT?
- AS YOU CAN SEE BY THE SIGN,
IT OPENED IN 1908.
IT USED TO BE
A STATE SCHOOL
FOR THE FEEBLE-MINDED
AND EPILEPTIC.
- O-M-G.
- AND THEN--
- FEEBLE-MINDED.
WE'RE GONNA FIT RIGHT IN.
- ARE YOU SCARED?
- YES,
'CAUSE I KNOW THIS IS REAL.
YOU GUYS DON'T,
AND YOU'RE LIKE, "OH,
IT'S ALL FUN AND GAMES." NO.
- OKAY,
YOU GUYS READY FOR THIS?
- NOW I HAVE TO PEE.
- LET THE BIGGER GUYS GO.
- YEAH, GET IN THERE.
- I THOUGHT THIS WAS DIFFERENT.
- BOO!
- [screams]
[bleep]!
[laughter]
[bleep].
- THERE'S MORE
SNOOKI AND JWOWW ON THE WAY,
AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
- REAL QUICK HISTORY
OF THIS BUILDING.
THIS IS THE ADMINISTRATIONS
BUILDING.
LIKE, WHERE YOU GUYS CAME IN,
THAT'S WHERE THEY WOULD DROP OFF
ALL THESE POOR KIDS, YOU KNOW,
PEOPLE WITH MENTAL ILLNESSES.
- THIS IS NOT
MY IDEAL DOUBLE DATE,
BUT I'VE ALWAYS WANTED
TO DO SOMETHING LIKE THIS...
- ME TOO.
- BECAUSE I'M JUST INTO, LIKE,
FREAKY PARANORMAL STUFF.
I'M, LIKE, A WEIRDO LIKE THAT.
THAT'S WHAT I READ IN MY BOOKS.
I READ PARANORMAL BOOKS.
[chuckles]
- [laughs]
- I READ.
[both laughing]
[metallic crashing]
[screams]
- [laughs]
- SORRY.
WAS THAT YOU, BABE?
- ROGER.
- BABE!
- I DIDN'T MEAN
TO MAKE THE SHOVEL FALL.
[laughter]
- WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
- CAN YOU BE DONE NOW?
I'M NOT KIDDING,
I'M GONNA HAVE
A HEART ATTACK.
I NEED JESUS, I NEED PRAYERS,
AND I NEED GANDHI.
- ARE YOU AIMING THAT
AT MY [bleep]?
[laughter]
WHAT'S THE READING?
- THEY'RE WARMER
THAN THE REST OF HER BODY.
[laughter]
- TOLD YOU.
- IF WE WERE IN A HORROR MOVIE
RIGHT NOW, I'D BE,
LIKE, THE FIRST ONE TO GO,
'CAUSE I HAVE THE BOOBS.
ACTUALLY, ALL FOUR OF US
WOULD BE DEAD FIRST,
'CAUSE WE ALL QUALIFY
FOR THE IDIOT
IN THE BEGINNING
THAT GOES DOWN.
- YOU'RE RECORDING?
- YEAH.
- THERE'S WATER HERE, BUT
WE'LL GET THROUGH IT QUICKLY.
- I CAN'T EVEN SEE.
[both laughing]
- I ALWAYS FEEL A HEAVINESS
ON MY CHEST, AND WE'LL GO...
- SHE DOES TOO.
- OVER INTO ONE OF THESE ROOMS.
- IF THERE'S ANYBODY HERE
WITH US,
CAN YOU MAKE
YOUR PRESENCE KNOWN?
- [makes fart noise]
[laughter]
- ROGER.
ROGER'S DEFINITELY
[bleep] AROUND TOO MUCH,
AND I CAN UNDERSTAND
A LITTLE JOKE HERE AND THERE,
BUT HE'S, LIKE,
MAKING FUN OF THE WHOLE THING,
AND I'M TRYING
TO TAKE THIS SERIOUSLY.
LIKE, THAT'S
KIND OF ANNOYING.
- CAN I ASK THE FIRST QUESTION?
- GO AHEAD.
- DO YOU WANT NICOLE
TO GET IN THERE WITH YOU?
- [starts]
- [laughs] STOP.
- ROGER, STOP.
- I WAS TOUCHED THREE TIMES WHEN
WE WENT JUST ON A QUICK WALK.
- TWO OF THOSE WERE ME.
[laughter]
- YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS
WITH THIS GUY.
- WHERE'S ROGER?
- YEAH, HE MAKES ME NERVOUS.
- ROGER?
- BAH!
- [starts]
- YOU HAD IT UP--AH!
[clanging]
[laughter]
- WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
- OH!
- [laughs]
- LITERALLY JUMPED
OUT OF MY SKIN.
- MY HEART GOES
DOWN TO MY VAGINA,
I WANT TO DIE, I'M LIKE, "WHAT
THE [bleep] JUST HAPPENED?"
I THOUGHT IT WAS THE EVIL GHOST,
LIKE, TRYING TO SCARE US.
- WHY DOES IT HAVE TO BE
YOUR VAGINA?
- I DON'T KNOW.
BUT IT WAS ROGER.
[screams]
- WHAT?
- SOMEONE JUST BLEW
ON MY NECK.
[shuddering scream]
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- OH, MY GOD!
- WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
- [whimpers]
ALL OF A SUDDEN, I FELT, LIKE,
THIS THING, LIKE, GO UP MY BACK.
IT WAS NOT JIONNI.
I KNOW WHAT A HAND FEELS LIKE.
IT WAS NOT A HAND.
IT WAS LIKE AIR.
IT WASN'T YOU,
I KNOW IT.
JIONNI, WAS IT YOU?
- NO, IT WASN'T ME.
- YO, CHECK THIS OUT.
THERE'S A LITTLE KIDDIE POOL
BACK HERE.
- WHY DON'T WE DO A SESSION
RIGHT NEXT TO IT?
- ARE YOU SCARED?
- DO YOU WANT YOUR MOMMY?
- I'M A MOM,
YOU CAN TOUCH ME.
- HERE, WHY DON'T WE CHECK
THE AUDIO ON THAT?
- [recorded voice]
DO YOU WANT YOUR MOMMY?
- [garbled voice] MOMMY.
- I'M A MOMMY--
- HOLY--
- WHAT'D IT SAY?
- OF EVERYTHING I'VE HEARD
THUS FAR,
THAT IS THE BEST ONE.
- WHAT'D IT SAY? WHAT'D IT SAY?
- IT SOUNDED LIKE "MOMMY."
- WE HEARD THE GHOST
SAY "MOMMY,"
AND THAT JUST
MAKES EVERYTHING WORSE.
IT JUST CLARIFIES,
YOU KNOW,
THAT THERE ARE GHOSTIES
IN THIS WORLD.
- HONEST QUESTION:
WOULD YOU SPEND THE NIGHT
IN THERE BY YOURSELF?
- NO. HELL, NO.
- I WOULD.
- BY YOURSELF? NO.
- I NEVER--NEVER
IN A MILLION YEARS.
- IT'S POINTLESS.
- I WOULDN'T.
SO WE NEED TO GET THE HELL
OUT OF HERE,
'CAUSE I DON'T WANT
THE EVIL SPIRIT,
LIKE,
THROWING [bleep] AT US.
OH, MY GOD.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- I'M JUST SCARED.
- [growls]
- [screams]
YOU'RE SUCH [bleep].
I SWEAR TO GOD.
- BYE.
[thunder crashing]
- SORRY WE WERE SO LATE.
- THIS IS FOR YOU.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- THANK YOU AGAIN.
- YES.
- THANK YOU.
IT WAS VERY NICE TO MEET YOU.
- ARE YOU READY FOR BED?
- YES.
FIRST NIGHT OF LORENZO
WITH THE BABYSITTER.
- HOW'D YOU FEEL? IT WAS
PRETTY COMFORTABLE, RIGHT?
- I WAS GOOD.
- SHE REALLY WASN'T BAD.
- WHY, 'CAUSE YOU LIKE HER?
- OH, MY GOD.
- GO BE WITH THE BABYSITTER
THEN.
- [sighs]
GOOD NIGHT.
- GET OFF.
- SHUT UP.
- TURN OFF THE LIGHT.
- [groans]
- THANK YOU FOR GOING WITH ME.
- WELL.
- DID YOU GET SCARED AT ALL?
- NO. A LITTLE BIT.
I GOT MORE SCARED
OF THE THUNDER.
- BAH!
- STOP.
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
- [laughs]
- HEY, DON'T BE A [bleep].
- YOU WANT TO GO PLAY PAINTBALL?
- WE GOTTA DO IT
BEFORE THE GIRLS GET BACK.
WHERE ARE YOU, ROGER?
[shooting paintballs]
- GOT YOU, BITCH!
- WHERE'D THEY GO?
- [gasps]
JANIS IS TRYING
TO SAVE HER SON RIGHT NOW.
- WE'RE GOING TO A.C.
- OH, MY GOD.
- IN THE BACK OF JIONNI'S MIND
HE'S LIKE,
"I HOPE SHE DOESN'T GET
TOO DRUNK"...
[screaming and laughing]
AND, YOU KNOW,
"KISSES HER GIRLFRIENDS."
I NEED JESUS.