- IT'S NICE TO BE BACK AT
THE SHORE.
IT'S PERFECT.
- OUR SUMMER NOW
IS OFFICIALLY STARTED.
I'M EXCITED.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE A BLAST.
- I KNOW.
- OH, MY GOD!
- [screams]
YOU DID IT, DOM.
- HE'S GONNA WALK THIS SUMMER.
- I'M GONNA CRY.
- DO YOU WANT TO WRITE DOWN
OUR PROBLEMS?
- MAYBE WE COULD START IT.
I'M BEING VERY OPTIMISTIC
ABOUT THIS THERAPY.
THE ULTIMATE GOAL WOULD BE
TO GET HELP.
- AND NOT KILL EACH OTHER.
- AND NOT KILL EACH OTHER,
YES.
[Icona Pop's I Love It]
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT,
I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* *
* I DON'T CARE *
[rock music playing]
- REMEMBER WHEN I WAS PREGNANT
WITH LORENZO?
HE'S WALKING NOW.
- HE'S GROWING UP TOO FAST.
- LORENZO'S FIRST BIRTHDAY
IS COMING UP,
AND IT'S EXCITING.
- OH, CAN'T WAIT.
- AND IT WENT BY SO QUICK,
AND IT'S SO SAD.
MY LITTLE BABY'S GROWING UP.
- HE'S GONNA BE ONE.
OH, MY GOD.
- WE NEED A THEME.
- DINOSAUR THEME?
- IF IT'S A DINOSAUR PARTY,
WE GOT TO DRESS AS DINOSAURS.
- I GOT TO WALK AROUND WITH
MY ARMS LIKE THIS?
- PTERODACTYL?
- THAT'S T-REX.
- I'M LIKE--[chuckles]
- OH, [bleep], HERE WE GO.
- [dinosaur howl]
- WHAT THE [bleep]...
[laughter]
WAS THAT?
- [dinosaur howl]
- [laughs] [bleep]
- ALL RIGHT, NO DINOSAURS, THEN.
PIRATES THEME?
- YES!
PIRATE THEME.
- I LOVE PIRATES.
- ARR.
- ALL RIGHTY, KIDS!
[laughs]
- YOU'RE GONNA SCARE EVERYBODY
IF YOU TALK LIKE THAT.
- AHOY, MATEYS!
[laughter]
I NEED PIRATE LESSONS.
YO HO, YO HO!
[laughter]
- BING, DONE.
PIRATE THEME.
YO, IT'S GONNA BE SICK.
- ARR. [laughs]
- YOU JUST BLEW A BOOGER OUT
OF YOUR NOSTRIL.
- I DID?
- YEP, YEP.
[upbeat music]
* *
- LET'S GO.
SO TODAY,
WE HAVE ANOTHER THERAPY SESSION.
- OUR LAST ONE.
- KEYWORD BEING "LAST."
- WELL, WELCOME BACK.
AS YOU KNOW,
THIS IS OUR LAST SESSION.
- DOES THAT MEAN WE'RE CURED?
- WELL, WE'LL DISCUSS THAT.
- [laughs]
- WE'LL SEE HOW WE'RE DOING.
WERE THERE ANY THINGS DRAMATIC
IN THE TIME
SINCE I LAST SAW YOU?
- ROGER AND MY BEST FRIEND'S
SIGNIFICANT OTHER
PREPARED US A FRENCH, LIKE,
FIVE-COURSE...
- GREAT.
- ROMANTIC DINNER WITH...
- MM-HMM.
- ROSE PETALS,
AND CHOCOLATE SOUFFLES, AND...
- FANTASTIC.
- HE WAS TRYING, UM,
BUT I DIDN'T HAVE SEX
WITH HIM AFTER IT.
- WHAT SHE WANTS,
I WAS DOING THAT.
I WAS DOING EXACTLY THAT.
MORE TOUCHY, MORE FEELING,
MORE LOVEY
MORE AFFECTION, MORE--AND
I WAS DOING ALL THOSE THINGS.
AND IT MADE IT EXTREMELY AWKWARD
FOR HER,
BECAUSE THAT'S NOT REALLY ME.
- SO, WHAT I'VE LEARNED,
AND WHAT I'VE COME TO
THE AGREEMENT IS,
I DON'T NECESSARILY
WANT HIM TO BE MORE ROMANTIC,
I WANT HIM TO JUST PAY ATTENTION
TO ME,
WHICH HE HAS BEEN DOING.
- AND THAT--AND THAT'S FAIR.
- AND I DON'T LIKE THE ROMANCE,
THE WEIRD, TOUCHY-FEELY,
MUMBO-JUMBO.
- MM-HMM.
- CAN YOU TRY TO SUM UP
WHAT YOU'VE GOTTEN OUT
OF THESE SESSIONS?
- I LEARNED THAT GOING ABOVE
AND BEYOND
AND DOING THOSE LITTLE THINGS,
LIKE COOKING ROMANTIC DINNERS
AND STUFF,
STILL WON'T GET YOU LAID.
THAT'S WHAT I'VE LEARNED.
- HAVE WE SOLVED EVERYTHING?
- UH, NO.
- [chuckles]
I FEEL LIKE EVERY SINGLE ISSUE
IS STILL AN ISSUE WITH US,
AND IT'S ALWAYS GONNA BE
AN ISSUE WITH US
FOR THE REST OF OUR LIVES,
BUT WE CAN MAKE
IMPROVEMENTS ON IT,
AND WE CAN MAKE GAINS ON IT.
- WELL, MY DOOR'S ALWAYS OPEN.
YOU HAVE MY PHONE NUMBER.
- JENNI'S DOOR IS NEVER OPEN.
- IT SURE AS HELL AIN'T NOW.
- ESPECIALLY THE BACK ONE.
- SEE WHAT I DEAL WITH?
- IT'S BEEN A PLEASURE.
both: THANK YOU.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR COMING.
- I THINK THERAPY WENT WELL.
WE HAVE NO REGRETS,
BUT, YOU KNOW, IT'S TIME TO END
IT AND--AND TRY IT ON OUR OWN.
YOU'RE MINE, AND I'M YOURS,
AND WE'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE,
BUT REGARDLESS, WE SH--
WE ALL HAVE OUR PROBLEMS,
AND I ACCEPT YOURS
AND YOU ACCEPT MINE.
- RIGHT, SO WHY'D WE HAVE
TO GO TO THERAPY?
- SHUT UP.
- [laughs]
- GOD.
- ALL THE BEST.
- APPRECIATE IT.
YOU MAY SEE US AGAIN.
- YES, THAT YOU MAY.
- TERRIFIC.
[line ringing]
- HELLO?
- HELLO, MATEY!
- HELLO.
WHAT YOU DOING?
- I WAS JUST TALKING TO JIONNI
ABOUT LORENZO'S BIRTHDAY.
AND IT'S A PIRATE THEM, AND
WE HAVE TO GO GET DECORATIONS,
SO, UM, JIONNI CAN'T GO
BECAUSE LORENZO IS SLEEPING,
SO WILL YOU GO WITH ME?
- YEAH.
- AND, UM, WILL YOU DO
A CLOWN TESTING WITH ME?
I WANT ME AND JENNI
TO DRESS UP AS CLOWNS
FOR LORENZO TO SEE IF
HE'S SCARED OF CLOWNS BEFORE
HIS BIRTHDAY PARTY.
I WOULD FEEL LIKE
A [bleep] ASS[bleep]
IF I HIRED A CLOWN TO COME
TO LORENZO'S BIRTHDAY
AND HE WAS TERRIFIED
AND STARTED CRYING,
AND IT RUINS HIS WHOLE BIRTHDAY.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
I'LL PICK YOU UP IN FIVE.
- ALL RIGHT, I'LL HURRY UP THEN.
- AYE, AYE, MATEY.
[upbeat music]
* *
AYE, AYE, MATEY.
[crash, beeping]
- OOH!
- I MEAN, YOU KNOW--
- I JUST HIT SOMETHING.
I JUST HIT SOMETHING.
- IT--YOU JUST HIT THE CURB,
IT'S FINE.
- OH, MY GOD.
[laughs]
- SKULL BANDANAS.
OH, 12 PIRATE EYE PATCHES.
VALUE PACK.
- FOR LORENZO'S FIRST BIRTHDAY,
I'M THINKING EVERYBODY DRESSED
UP IN PIRATE COSTUMES.
EN GARDE.
I CAN'T SEE.
I'LL GET YOU, MY PRETTY!
- AAH!
- OH, THAT'S A WITCH, HOLD ON.
- [laughs]
I FEEL LIKE WE LOOK AWESOME
AS PIRATES.
- YEAH.
I MEAN, I'M NOT
THE BEST SWORD FIGHTER,
BUT WE'RE PRETTY AT LEAST.
HELLO, JENNI.
- [chuckles]
IT'S OBAMA.
- [laughs] WHAT?
FREEDOM IS IMPORTANT.
- I DID NOT INHALE,
AND I DID NOT HAVE SEX
WITH THAT GIRL.
- [laughs]
YES, YOU DID!
[laughter]
- OH, MY GOD.
I HOPE NO ONE SAW THAT.
[rock music]
* *
- WE'RE GONNA BE CLOWNS!
- HOLD ON.
- OOH!
- I DON'T WANT TO DRESS LIKE
A [bleep] CLOWN,
BUT I WILL FOR MY GODSON.
HOW'S THAT?
- YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, BLOW ME UP.
[fan whirring]
EW!
[laughter]
OH, MY GOD, I'M GONNA BE
A FAT CLOWN.
- [honks]
- WHY DO I GOT TO BE
THE FAT CLOWN?
IT'S GOT TO BE
THE SHORT, FAT ONE.
- A [bleep] MULLET?
[both chuckling]
- OH, MY GOD.
- SEE THAT, YOU ARE SO--
I FEEL A DRAFT BACK HERE.
- YOU LOOK LIKE A BOY.
- I WOULD NEVER BE A CLOWN
AS A JOB.
- NO.
- THEY'RE WEIRD.
- I'M JUST DOING THIS
FOR MY SON.
- YEAH.
- AND EVEN IF I'M GOOD AT IT--
- I DON'T GIVE A [bleep].
- WHO THE [bleep] WANTS
TO BE A CLOWN?
- [bleep], NO.
I'M TOO MUCH OF A BITCH
TO BE A CLOWN.
- NAH, I'D RATHER BE PRETTY.
[horn squeaking]
WE SHOULD TWERK AS CLOWNS.
[laughter]
- I THINK NICOLE IS
THE FIRST ONE TO INVENT
THE CLOWN TWERK.
[horns squeaking]
HOLD ON.
[laughs]
- OH, MY GOD.
[horns squeaking]
WHAT THE F--
WHAT ARE THESE
TWO GOOFBALLS DOING?
- HI, LORENZO!
- HI!
- [laughs]
[horn squeaking]
- HERE WE GO!
I FEEL LIKE IT'S A MYTH THAT
BABIES ARE SCARED OF CLOWNS.
I THINK LORENZO IS GOING TO
BE FINE WITH THE CLOWNS.
- MY SON'S NOT VERY ENTERTAINED,
CLOWNS.
[horns squeaking]
OH, MY--CAN I HAVE
MY MONEY BACK?
THEY LOOK LIKE A BUNCH
OF WHACKADOOS,
DANCING LIKE GOOFBALLS,
HONKING THE HORN.
JENNI'S RHYTHM IS WAY OFF.
NICOLE AT LEAST
LOOKS LIKE A CUTE CLOWN.
JENNI IS JUST SCARING
THE [bleep] OUT OF EVERYBODY.
I'M GETTING SCARED OF JENNI.
- QUICK, GRAB MY NOSE.
YOU GOT MY NOSE!
- [cries]
- UH-OH.
- OH, YOU'RE SCARING HIM.
- AW.
- YOU'RE SCARING HIM!
- [cries]
- AW!
- IT'S THE MULLET!
- CLOWN TRICK'S OVER.
- DOM, IT'S ME!
- CLOWNS, THE PARTY'S OVER.
- IT'S ME, IT'S ME, IT'S OKAY.
- IT'S THE MULLET.
- [cries]
- JENNI, TAKE 'EM OFF.
- CLOWN, THE PARTY'S OVER.
GET OUT!
[laughter]
GET OUT.
- WE'RE SORRY.
- IT'S OKAY.
COME ON.
- WHAT DID YOU DO?
- I JUST LET HIM--
- COME ON.
- HE GRABBED THE WIG.
- GET OUT, CLOWN PARTY IS OVER.
- YOU SCARED HIM!
- [laughs] I DIDN'T DO ANY--
AAH!
[horn squeaking]
- CHEAP-ASS CLOWNS.
WE'LL STICK TO PIRATES.
- LET'S GO.
- WALK OF SHAME?
- I'M ASHAMED.
I'M ASHAMED OF MYSELF.
[whistle, horn honk]
- * THE ONLY THING THAT
WE CHANGED IS OUR CLOTHES *
- * BAH BAH BAH *
- FORK ME.
- EW.
[laughs] SORRY.
- OOH.
- THERE'S SOME ONIONS
IN THE SALAD.
- HOW'D YOU KNOW
I WANTED ONIONS?
- 'CAUSE YOU ALWAYS PUT ONIONS
ON YOUR BURGER, AND PICKLE.
- HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
YOU KNOW ME?
- YEAH, A LITTLE BIT.
- WHAT'S MY FAVORITE NUMBER?
- THREE.
- [scoffs] MY GOD, FORGET IT.
- FIVE?
IT'S THREE OR FIVE.
IT'S FIVE.
- YOU WANT TO GET MARRIED,
YOU DON'T KNOW
MY FAVORITE NUMBER.
- IT'S FIVE!
- WHAT'S MY FAVORITE COLOR?
- BLUE.
- SURE YOU DON'T WANT TO ASK
THE AUDIENCE ON THAT ONE?
- [laughs]
- [coos]
- BLUE.
- WHAT'S MY FAVORITE ANIMAL?
- WHEN DID YOU TELL ME
YOU HAD A FAVORITE ANIMAL?
- YOU SHOULD JUST KNOW.
- LIZARD.
- A FRICKIN' LIZARD?
- [laughs]
- ARE YOU KIDDING?
- WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE ANIMAL?
LOOK, WE'RE GETTING TO KNOW
EACH OTHER. [laughs]
- OH, NOW WE'RE GETTING TO KNOW
EACH OTHER?
- [laughs]
- WE MAY HAVE TO POSTPONE
THIS WEDDING.
- NO, NO!
[geese honking]
- BABE, IT'S LORENZO'S BIRTHDAY.
IT'S LORENZO'S BIRTHDAY PARTY.
OH, YOUR BREATH STINKS.
- NO, IT DOESN'T!
- GO BRUSH YOUR TEETH.
COME ON, IT'S LORENZO'S--
LET'S GO WAKE LORENZO UP.
- OKAY.
TODAY IS LORENZO'S BIRTHDAY!
AND I'M SO EXCITED
MY BABY IS TURNING ONE.
I JUST HAVE ALL THESE EMOTIONS.
I'M NERVOUS, I'M SAD,
I'M ANXIOUS.
I MEAN, IT'S CRAZY.
- [laughs] DA-DA.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN HERE?
- HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
- LORENZO!
- DA-DA!
- BIRTHDAY BOY!
- OH, MY GOD.
- MY BABY'S ONE.
I CANNOT BELIEVE THAT MY BABY
IS TURNING ONE YEARS OLD.
EVERYTHING JUST WENT BY
SO QUICKLY.
I FEEL LIKE I JUST HAD HIM.
THIS IS IT, LORENZO.
YOU'RE HURTING ME.
- NICOLE, YOU'RE A PRO.
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH!
- [grunts]
- YAY!
- [laughs]
- A BOY, HEY!
- I'M JUST HAPPY.
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED A KID.
AND HE'S HERE, AND HE'S HEALTHY,
AND HE'S BEAUTIFUL.
[kisses]
MY LITTLE BOY.
- [coos]
- YOU'RE ONE TODAY.
- OH, YOU'RE SO BIG.
- I LOVE MY FAMILY.
- OH, MY GOD.
[rock music]
- WE DON'T HAVE A BABY ANYMORE.
- WHAT?
- WE HAVE A TODDLER.
- OH.
WHAT DO WE HAVE--
WE HAVE A LOT TO DO, NO?
WE GOT TO SET UP
THE PIRATE PLACE.
WHAT DO WE GOT LEFT?
PIN THE PAT...
- PIN THE PATCH ON A PIRATE.
- ON A PIRATE, RIGHT.
YOU WANT TO TRY
TO DRAW SOME PIRATES?
- YEAH, LET'S--LET'S DO
PIN THE PATCH ON THE PIRATE.
WHAT'S OUR NEXT THING?
- NICOLE AND I ARE BOTH GONNA
DRESS LIKE PIRATES,
SO ALL THE KIDS COULD PIN
THE PATCH ON 'EM.
- YOU THINK OTHER PARENTS DO
THIS FOR THEIR FIRST BIRTHDAY?
- UM, THEY DEFINITELY
GO ALL OUT,
BUT ACTUALLY DO IT THEMSELVES?
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
- I DON'T THINK SO.
WHATCHA THINKING?
- THAT EVERYTHING IS JUST
FOR LORENZO NOW.
IT'S NOT ABOUT US ANYMORE,
CUPCAKE.
- WELL, I'M FINE WITH THAT.
ALL ABOUT LORENZO NOW.
MY BABY.
I DO EVERYTHING FOR HIM.
- IT DOESN'T EVEN MATTER WHAT
WE WANT ANYMORE.
- NOPE.
- TIMES HAVE CHANGED.
- AGREED.
- FOR THE BOTH OF US.
- I LOVE IT.
I LOVE BEING A MOM.
- I'M SO PROUD OF NICOLE.
SHE IS AN UNBELIEVABLE MOTHER.
I-I CAN'T BE ANY PROUDER,
AND I CAN'T BE ANY HAPPIER.
- [laughs]
THAT WAS SO SWEET.
THIS IS MOMMY'S.
- YOU GO ON THAT SIDE.
- NO.
- SEE WHO HE GOES TO.
- THIS IS MOMMY'S,
THAT'S DADDY'S.
- LORENZO, WHOSE DO YOU WANT
FOR PIN THE PATCH ON THE PIRATE?
- WHOSE DO YOU LIKE?
- MINE OR MOMMY'S?
LORENZO, LORENZO,
YOU'RE NOT EVEN LOOKING!
- MINE OR MOMMY'S?
MINE OR MOMMY'S?
[both shouting, laughing]
- HI, BIG MAN.
COME HERE, COME HERE.
[laughter]
HERE! LORENZO, LOOK! WHEE!
- LORENZO, LORENZO.
WHO'S YOUR M--YOU CAN TOUCH IT.
- PIN THE PATCH.
- BACK UP.
- PIN THE PATCH ON THE PIRATE.
NO, LORENZO, LORENZO, LORENZO!
- [indistinct]
- NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
- COME ON, COME ON, YES!
YES!
- YOU DON'T LIKE MOMMY'S?
OF COURSE HE GOES
TO DADDY'S PIRATE,
BECAUSE LORENZO FAVORS JIONNI
IN THE FIRST PLACE,
SO I KNEW HE WAS GONNA WIN,
BUT I MEAN, THAT'S CHEATING.
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
MY PIRATE'S BETTER.
- * ONE, TWO, THREE *
* OH, CAN'T YOU SEE
THAT I NEED YOU? *
- I'M GONNA BE
AN ENGLISH PIRATE.
THIS IS FOR YOU.
- AH.
SO, TODAY IS LORENZO'S
FIRST BIRTHDAY,
AND IT'S TIME TO GET READY
FOR THE PIRATE PARTY.
ARR!
THIS ISN'T GONNA FIT,
I DON'T THINK. [grunts]
PULL DOWN ON THE BOTTOM.
- BIG BOY PROBLEMS.
- [sighs]
THIS IS LIKE SKINTIGHT.
- I'M ACTUALLY SUPER EXCITED
TO SEE ROGER IN
HIS PIRATE OUTFIT,
BECAUSE THIS SUMMER I HAVE
NOTICED HE HAS LOOKED HOT
IN COSTUME...
- OOH.
- BETWEEN A COWBOY, AND A CHEF,
NOW A PIRATE.
I'M TOTALLY INTO IT.
- YET NONE OF THOSE COSTUMES
WORKED.
- SHUT UP!
- WOW!
- I DON'T LOOK LIKE A PIRATE.
- YEAH, YOU DO.
- [fusses]
- YOU LOOK SEXY!
- MY PIRATE PANTS
ARE WAY TOO TIGHT.
I'M JUST A LITTLE UNCOMFORTABLE,
BUT I GOT TO DO IT
FOR LORENZO.
I GOT TO TAKE ONE FOR THE TEAM.
MY WEINER STICKS OUT TOO MUCH.
- I KNOW.
- MY PANTS COULD BE
ON BACKWARDS.
- YOU GOT A CAMEL TOE.
- I LOOK LIKE A [bleep] JABRONI.
- JIONNI, WRAP THE THING AROUND
YOUR PIECHE.
MY SCAROL IS HANGING OUT.
I LOOK [bleep] HORRIBLE.
I NEED BIGGER PANTS.
I LOOK LIKE A GIRL.
- NO, YOU DON'T!
- YES, I DO.
- BABE.
- I LOOK NOTHING LIKE A PIRATE.
- LET'S GO, YOU SWASHBUCKLER.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS,
BUT IT SOUNDS SEXY.
- SHIVER ME TIMBERS!
- * I GOT A KISS
AND YOU GOT OLDER *
- OH!
THIS IS [bleep] AWESOME.
IT'S GONNA BE SO FUN.
LOOK AT THE BOUNCE HOUSE!
SO WE GET TO PIRATE ADVENTURES,
AND THERE'S A PIRATE SHIP,
THERE'S PIRATE COSTUMES,
THERE'S GAMES,
AND I FEEL LIKE THE KIDS
ARE GONNA LOVE IT.
- * YO, YO, ROCK AND ROLL *
- YOU READY TO PARTY?
WHOO!
DID YOU PUT THE ARMY DUDES
IN THERE?
- YEAH.
- SO ME AND JIONNI NEED
TO SET UP THE GAMES
THAT WE MADE.
OUR TREASURE HUNT, OUR PIN
THE PATCH ON THE PIRATE GAME,
AND NOW WE'RE JUST WAITING FOR
OUR GUESTS TO GET THERE.
- HI, GUYS!
- AHOY!
- OH, MY GOD!
[laughter]
- HEY!
- HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- YOU LOOK GOOD.
- NEVER MIND.
- HOW YOU DOING?
- ARR!
- HEY, GUYS.
- HI!
- OH, MY GOD,
YOU GUYS LOOK SO CUTE!
I LOVE THIS PARTY.
IT'S SO CUTE.
IT'S LIKE THE PERFECT
ONE-YEAR-OLD'S PARTY.
- SHIVER ME TIMBERS.
- [laughs]
[upbeat music]
[indistinct chattering]
- SO ALL OF OUR GUESTS BEGIN
TO ARRIVE,
AND JIONNI'S SIBLINGS COME
WITH ALL
THEIR KIDS, AND THEIR WIVES,
AND HUSBANDS.
SO IT'S REALLY, REALLY NICE
TO SEE ALL THE FAMILY HERE,
AND, YOU KNOW, THEY GET
TO SEE LORENZO TURN ONE.
LET'S GO, MATEYS!
- GO GET SOME TREASURE.
SEE WHAT YOU CAN FIND.
PUT THIS PATCH ON
THE PIRATE'S EYE.
HO-HO!
- YAY! [claps]
all: WHOA!
- HOMERUN!
[all cheering]
- HERE YOU GO.
- KIDS THESE DAYS,
WITH THE VIOLENCE.
- OH, [bleep], THESE KIDS
ARE LIKE DEMANDING.
LIKE, THEY'RE LIKE STEPPING
OVER CANDY
AND ON EACH OTHER'S FINGERS,
LIKE, THEY WANT THAT CHOCOLATE.
- GOOD JOB, GUYS.
- I THOUGHT I WAS GONNA LOSE
AN ANKLE.
- EVERYBODY GET TO
THE CANNONS OVER HERE.
MAN THE CANNONS!
- MAN THE CANNONS!
- YO, GET OVER TO THE CANNONS!
WHOA!
all: WHOA!
- GET 'EM!
- PIRATES!
- LORENZO, GET 'EM!
[all shouting]
- BACK UP.
HE'S GONNA COME FOR YA!
LORENZO'S COMING FOR YA!
- OH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HE THREW IT IN THE WATER!
- ROGER!
- WE GOT IT MATES!
THIS IS AWESOME!
- YEAH, ROGER, WHOO!
[cheers and applause]
- ALL RIGHT, LORENZO,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO HELP US
UNLOCK THIS THING,
ALL RIGHT, BUDDY?
READY, ONE, TWO, THREE,
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- WHOA!
[all cheering]
[all shouting]
- YOU'VE GOT THE TREASURE!
EVERYONE, AND HE FOUND
THE TREASURE!
[cheers and applause]
- YAY!
all: WHOO!
- LOOK AT THAT, REAL COINS.
YOU GET MONEY, DUDE.
PUT YOUR HANDS IN.
COME ON, HERE.
ON THE COUNT OF THREE,
WE'RE GONNA SING HAPPY BIRTHDAY
TO LORENZO.
COME ON IN.
- READY?
- COME OVER HERE.
all: ONE, TWO, THREE.
all: HAPPY BIRTHDAY, LORENZO!
- WHOO!
- GREAT JOB, KIDS, GREAT JOB!
- THANK YOU.
- THERE'S MORE SNOOKI AND JWOWW
ON THE WAY.
- AND IT CONTINUES NOW.
[indistinct chatter]
- COME HERE.
IT'S YOUR CAKE!
- READY?
ONE, TWO, THREE.
all: HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
[cheers and applause]
- MY BABY'S NOT A BABY ANYMORE.
LORENZO DEFINITELY GREW UP.
LIKE, HE CAME TO THE SHORE
A BABY,
AND HE IS LEAVING A TODDLER.
IT'S OKAY.
YOU CAN CRY.
[all awwing]
I'M SO SAD.
HE'S NOT A BABY ANYMORE.
- HE'S STILL YOUR BABY.
- HE'S A BABY.
- JIONNI SAID HE'S GONNA GO
TO KARMA AND GET GIRLS.
[laughter]
SO, THE PARTY WAS
A HUGE SUCCESS.
ALL THE KIDS HAD SUCH
A GOOD TIME.
THE PARENTS LOVED IT,
THE FAMILY LOVED IT.
- YOUR BIRTHDAY IS THE PERFECT
WAY TO END EVERY SUMMER.
- WE ENDED PRETTY GOOD, RIGHT?
- DID YOU KNOW THAT?
- THIS WAS THE BEST WAY
TO END THE SUMMER.
- AND DO YOU KNOW WHAT
MY FAVORITE ONE'S GONNA BE?
WHEN YOU TURN 21!
- UH-OH.
- OH!
- SERIOUSLY.
- UH-OH.
- HOW OLD ARE YOU GONNA BE?
50?
- 35.
- I'LL BE DEAD IN A GRAVE.
- [chuckles] BITCH.
- YOU'LL BE 35?
- YEAH.
AND SO WILL YOU.
- HEY, IT WAS GREAT--
- WHEN HE'S 21?
- YEAH, AND SO WILL YOU.
- NO, IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
- EXACTLY.
- YOU'LL BE 60.
- OH, I SEE WHERE
YOU'RE GOING WITH THIS.
- ONE DAY, LORENZO'S GONNA BE
AN ADULT,
AND I CAN LOOK BACK AND BE LIKE,
"I REMEMBER YOUR FIRST
BIRTHDAY."
- WE'RE GONNA
BE LIKE 50-SOMETHING, 60.
- [sighs]
- GOD!
- 40s, ASS[bleep].
- WHATEVER.
- [chuckles]
- WOW, LOOK AT THIS.
[all sighing]
- THIS IS GORGEOUS.
- WHAT A WAY TO END
THE SUMMER, HUH?
- WOW.
- HUH? HUH, SCALLYWAGS?
- I GOT BIT.
- YOU GUYS LOOKED SO CUTE AROUND
ALL THE KIDS TODAY.
I LOVED IT.
both: I LOVE KIDS.
- YOU COULD HAVE
A LITTLE ONE NEXT YEAR...
- [laughs] MAYBE.
- AT LORENZO'S SECOND PARTY.
- NEVER SAY NEVER.
- YOU COULD TOO.
- YEAH, I COULD.
YOU NEVER KNOW.
I CANNOT WAIT FOR JENNI
TO GET KNOCKED UP.
- I WANT TO HAVE
A CHILD BEFORE 30,
SO THAT MEANS NEXT YEAR
I HAVE TO BE PREGNANT.
- WHOO!
- OH, MY GOD.
- EVENTUALLY, YOU'RE GONNA
GET MARRIED.
- MAYBE, MOST LIKELY, YEAH.
- GOOD.
- "MAYBE, MOST LIKELY, YEAH"?
- [laughs]
- THE ULTIMATE GOAL WAS JUST
TO BE HAPPY,
AND BE WITH EACH OTHER,
AND JUST TURN THAT NEXT PAGE
TO THAT NEXT CHAPTER IN
OUR LIVES
AND--AND DO IT TOGETHER,
YOU KNOW, NO MATTER WHAT.
JUST BEING--
- WHEREVER WE ARE,
WE'RE IN IT TOGETHER.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- NOW THAT THE SUMMER IS OVER,
WE'RE GOING BACK TO
THE BASEMENT.
- YEAH, I MEAN,
WE GOT OUR HOUSE IN ORDER.
YOU KNOW, WE SAID ROUGHLY
BY NEXT SUMMER,
AND THEN WE GOT, UH,
OUR WEDDING, SO...
WE HAVE A LOT.
- I CAN'T WAIT TO GET MARRIED.
- WE HAVE A LOT COMING UP
AND THE WHOLE NINE.
- I CAN'T WAIT FOR NEXT YEAR,
'CAUSE I FEEL LIKE IF THIS YEAR
WAS THIS GOOD,
NEXT YEAR'S GONNA BE
SO MUCH BETTER.
- MM-HMM.
WE DID A LOT OF FUN [bleep]
THIS SUMMER.
- A LOT.
- WE HAD AN AWESOME SUMMER,
AND, YOU KNOW, WE'RE GLAD WE GOT
TO SHARE IT WITH YOU GUYS.
- REGARDLESS OF WHAT'S GONNA
HAPPEN NEXT YEAR,
I HOPE I'M WITH YOU GUYS.
- I HOPE I'M WITH YOU TOO.
- [kisses]
AND SO DOES LORENZO.
- LOOK AT HIS TEETH.
- YEAH.
- LOOK AT NICOLE'S.
- HE'S LIKE--
[laughter]
- STUPID, ROGER.
- LET'S JUST SAY,
"TO BE CONTINUED."
- YES.
WE LOVE YOU...
- AND...
both: WE'LL SEE YOU LATER.
- [kisses]
- MWAH.