[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Okay, everyone, settle down.
[indistinct chatter]
I'd like to introduce
Mid-Wilshire's
newest sergeant, Lucy Chen.
- Hi.
It's nice to meet you all.
- Sergeant Chen will
join us on night shift.
She'll be in charge of Team 54.
- Dream Team, what?
[whooping]
- All right, settle down.
Officer Hall, I trust you'll
give your new sergeant
the respect that she's earned.
- Oh, you know it, boss.
Happy to have a new grown-up
in charge, Sergeant Chen.
- Well, thank you.
I'm eager to join
the Dream Team
and hit the ground running.
- ♪ I'm on a lost train
going faster than I'd like ♪
- Pending units, 911 unknown,
2468 Stanley.
Hang up on callback.
Pending units.
- Control, Lincoln-300,
I'm right around the corner.
Attach me to that.
♪ ♪
- Control, Lincoln-300, Code 4.
Child playing
with the landline.
- Copy, Code 4.
- ♪ So bad ♪
- Pending units, 4-15,
fight outside Pomelo Diner.
Two men in a physical.
- Lincoln-300 attach.
Thank you.
[Shane Guerrette's
"Lost Without You"]
- ♪ Lost, lost without ♪
- Control, Lincoln-300, Code 4.
All suspects GOA.
- Copy.
Suspects gone at Pomelo Diner.
Pending units, silent alarm.
11201 Wilcox.
- Lincoln-300 attach.
- ♪ Before my eyes ♪
- Lincoln-300, Code 4,
false alarm, 11201 Wilcox.
- ♪ And it don't change
not a thing ♪
- Control,
can you give me a 10-21?
- Copy, incoming.
[phone rings]
- Hey, my team is not
showing up to calls,
and my computer shows them
all at one location.
Can you check that
the GPS system is working
and confirm that the last call
dispatched to there?
- Of course.
I'll send the GPS status
and call history to your box.
- Thank you.
- ♪ Lost, lost without ♪
♪ ♪
- Sergeant on deck!
- You guys have been here
the whole time?
Sleeping?
- To be clear,
I wasn't sleeping.
- Because you're the lookout.
Now I know why you're
called the Dream Team.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[exhales]
- Hey.
- Good morning.
- For you.
For me, it is wine-o-clock.
- Tough day?
Night?
- Yes, to both.
Man, I can't believe
how exhausted I am
after only one night shift.
Like--
- At least you're a sergeant
now, bossing people around?
- Hardly.
You know--you know, they
call themselves the Dream Team
because they sleep all night?
- Oh, yikes.
Well, I know you'll find
a way to motivate them.
- Mm.
- Hey, roomie question.
- Yeah.
- I mean, should I expect
to see Tim around more often?
- What? Why?
- Well, I mean, no, nothing.
It's just that, I mean,
we might wanna make a schedule.
With Rodge on tour,
we're fine for now.
I mean, but we might run
into hot water issues.
- Are you just assuming that
Tim and I are back together?
- You're a sergeant,
he's a sergeant.
Problem solved.
- There were a lot
of other problems.
And we still need to have
a serious conversation
before anything
more can happen.
- Right.
So what are you waiting for?
- We're on opposite schedules.
You know, when I'm awake,
Lucy's asleep, and vice versa.
- That's a lie.
You cross over
at shift changes.
You could find the time
if you wanted to.
- Of course I want to.
It's just... [sighs]
I don't wanna pressure her.
You know, I'm trying to be
respectful of the fact
that I'm the one
who broke her heart.
- Well, you might
break it again
if you leave her hanging
too long.
- [sighs]
Hey.
What's that?
- Oh, this is my wall of Oscar.
Only it's not up on a wall,
because then
it'd be a crazy wall.
And I'm not crazy, I'm just--
- Obsessed?
- Yeah.
No. Well, yeah.
This--Oscar Hutchinson is
the worst person in the world.
I just need him behind bars.
I don't find that
to be irrational.
- It's not.
But do you pull this out
and stare at it
every time I leave the house?
- No.
No.
I just--whenever I get a hit
from one of the law enforcement
databases, I pull it out,
and I add it
to the Oscar chart.
- Well, what was today's alert?
- Oh, Sal Detto
was murdered yesterday
at a motel in Barstow.
Sal and Oscar
used to be running buddies
back in the late '90s.
They were part of a three-man
crew that stole $10 million
worth of diamonds from
a jewelry store in Las Vegas.
- But if Oscar had
that kind of cash,
why wasn't he living
on a beach somewhere?
- Because when the crew was on
their way back to Los Angeles,
the cops caught on to them.
So they split up,
managed to hide out.
Oscar escaped,
but Sal Detto was arrested,
as was the third member
of the crew, Reggie Acosta.
But the diamonds
were never recovered.
- So they hid them
before the arrest?
- One of them did.
And I think it
was Reggie Acosta.
- Because Oscar wasn't
rolling in money afterwards.
- Exactly.
And Sal Detto got out
of prison five years ago.
He's been living
in an SRO ever since.
Logically, the only one who
knows where those diamonds
are hidden is Reggie Acosta.
- When does Reggie
get out of prison?
- Today is the day Reggie
Acosta gets out of prison.
Now, it's clear to me
that Sal was going
to Barstow to wait for Reggie.
Stands to reason Oscar
would do the same thing.
But knowing Oscar,
he killed Sal
so he wouldn't have to share.
And it's more than likely
he's going to kill Reggie
once he retrieves the diamonds.
- Did you reach out
to the Feds about this theory?
- Well, Garza was kind enough
not to laugh at my face.
U.S. Marshals, not so much.
- I mean,
it's definitely a stretch.
But since you feel
so strongly about it,
I will grant you
a temporary duty assignment.
Congratulations.
You are officially Detective
Nolan for the next 48 hours.
Give Barstow PD a heads up,
and take Harper with you.
- Yes, sir.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Get this off my desk.
[clattering]
- Just leave. Just leave.
- It's all just so confusing.
Like, I know I've been out
of the game for a minute,
but I didn't think
I was gonna have to learn
a whole new language
just to be on the dating apps.
- Like what?
- Like what does "ethically
non-monogamous" mean?
- It's when people
in the relationship
are all dating and/or
sleeping with other people,
with the consent
of everyone involved.
- Well, what if I just wanna
be monogamous, monogamous?
- That's still allowed.
- Cool.
Well, how do I find it?
- Um...
you--oh, you specify
under Intentions.
Would you say you're looking
for a short-term relationship,
long-term relationship,
long-term open to short,
or short-term open to long?
- Well, that's--
that's a lot going on.
- You know, back in my day,
we just went to bars.
- Oh, yes, sir.
Well, I was just
filling out, you know,
a profile or two, but maybe
nothing'll come from it.
- As long as you don't
put down that you're a cop.
- Why? It's what I do.
- Which would be fine
if you were
an accountant or a realtor.
Look, people have very
strong opinions about cops.
Some people hate us,
won't give you a chance.
And some people love us
too much, which is just as bad.
- Yeah, well, we had badge
bunnies back in Sugarland--
I mean, not that I have any
personal experience with them
because I was with Camilla
for so long.
- Look, it shouldn't be
on your profile.
- All right, well,
I'll take it off.
You know how to do it.
- Let's go, Boot.
- All right.
[animal chirping]
- Thanks again for doing this.
I know getting Oscar
is a long shot.
- Yeah, I'm happy to help.
And honestly, having a bed
to myself for a whole night
more than makes up for it.
- [chuckles]
- And what a crazy year
it has been.
- You have no idea.
Strike that.
You actually were knocked
around worse than we were.
- Yeah.
But we all made it through,
mostly intact.
- Mostly.
- You know, I'm actually
feeling excited.
Getting back in the dating game
should be fun.
- Man, dating in LA
is the worst.
You haven't even started yet.
- I was actually hoping
for a little encouragement.
- From me?
- Right.
[notification chimes]
Hey, I already
matched with someone.
She's, uh, she's pretty, right?
- That photo is
probably 20 years old.
- Man, you know what?
Sometimes talking to you
is like trying to bag flies.
I don't know how
Lucy survived it.
- Is that right?
- Oh, my--my apologies.
My--my brain malfunctioned.
No disrespect intended.
[tires screech]
- You know what?
Disrespect taken.
You've clearly forgotten
the power dynamic in this shop.
I am not your friend.
I am your TO--
with the ability to bounce you
from this program
for any reason.
And lack of respect
is at the top of my list.
- Yes, sir.
Uh, I completely understand.
It won't happen again,
I promise.
- 7-Adam-100, 2-11 in progress
at Los Angeles Savings Bank
on South Coronado.
Single suspect.
- Saved by the crime.
Copy, show us responding.
Send three additional units,
Code 3.
Shut down lights
two blocks out.
[sirens wailing]
- [panting]
Oh, God!
- [chuckles]
20 bucks says the guy
leaking money
is our bank robber.
- I love it when
the job is easy.
- [panting]
[siren chirping]
- You got any weapons on you?
- [panting]
Just a plastic one.
Sweatshirt pocket.
- Keep your hands
where I can see them.
- [panting] No, please.
You don't understand.
I only robbed the bank
to save my girlfriend.
She needs a heart transplant
immediately.
She'll die without it.
[dramatic music]
- The only doctor who can
save Boyana is in Switzerland.
To get there from her village
in Bulgaria will cost 5,000.
And the procedure itself
is nearly 50,000.
- So you robbed a bank?
- I know it was wrong.
But she has revolving myeloma.
It's a rare disorder.
Her blood type keeps changing.
A transplant is
near impossible.
- Is that a thing?
- If it is, it's news to me.
- How did you meet Boyana?
- Social media.
She liked one of my posts,
and we just hit it off.
- So you two haven't
met in person?
- No, we just talk online.
- Hmm.
You notice anything weird
about her hands?
- No.
- Seven fingers on one
and three on the other?
[quirky music]
- Okay.
Like a birth defect?
- No.
Like this is AI-generated.
Revolving myeloma isn't real.
People's blood type
doesn't magically change.
Someone posing as Boyana
is scamming you.
- That's--
No.
No, you're wrong.
- I'm not.
But you've committed
multiple felonies,
and you're going to jail.
Someone will come
take you back to holding.
- I robbed a bank.
[sighs]
My wife's gonna be so pissed.
- His wife?
- Still excited to jump
into the dating pool, Boot?
- Less and less.
- Well, clearly,
he's being catfished.
- Or he created the photo
in case he got caught.
- Well, he seems
genuinely heartbroken.
Dumb as it is,
he thought he was saving her.
[birds cawing]
[tires screech]
[drone whirring]
- Whoa!
Damn, that was close.
- Sorry.
- [chuckles]
- Maid found Sal Detto inside
around 9:00 yesterday morning.
ME put time of death
between 2:00 and 5:00 a.m.
Victim checked in the day
before, but no complaints.
Of course, we ran him out.
And he's got a criminal history
since before I was born.
- You get statements
from any of the other guests?
- No one saw or heard anything.
And all the security cameras
are broken out here.
- You up to speed
on our suspect?
- Oscar Hutchinson. Yes, sir.
Photos have circulated
to local and state police.
We'll keep our eyes out.
- Any other motels in the area?
- No, sir.
This is the only spot
for 40 miles.
Is there anything else
I can do for you guys?
- No, we're gonna set up here.
- Yes, ma'am.
- All right, Detective Nolan.
What do you see?
[suspenseful music]
- Okay, well,
nothing is really knocked over.
Our victim was lying in the
bed, presumably watching TV.
Hears a knock at the door,
walks straight to the door.
Assailant comes in, stabs him.
He staggers back,
lands there, face up.
- It makes sense that
he would open the door
for Oscar, a familiar face.
- And viciously stabbing
an old friend to death
is so very Oscar.
- Yeah.
All right, get us a couple
rooms with a vantage point.
- You got it.
[drone whirring]
[giggling]
[upbeat music playing]
♪ ♪
- Dash, if you fly that camera
over those girls at the pool,
you will be grounded for life.
- Mom, I'm making a movie.
Fine.
- Hey.
- I'm not supposed
to talk to strangers.
- Oh, well, I am a cop.
- Sweet.
Will you tell my mom that
it's perfectly legal for me
to film in a public place?
- Uh, no.
Were you here yesterday?
- No.
I just got here
a couple hours ago.
Mom's latest midlife crisis.
She thinks she's gonna be
a blackjack dealer in Vegas.
- Good a job as any.
- Won't last.
Month ago, she was convinced
we'd make a fortune
breeding Bengal cats.
- I heard that!
- I love you.
Are you here because
of the murder?
Because if you want,
I could keep an eye out
and record anyone
that looks shady.
Although, it's a motel
on the way to Vegas.
Everyone looks shady.
- Well, that's not necessary,
nor is it safe.
But if you see anything,
give me a call?
[drone whirring]
[jackhammer rattling, banging]
[engine revving]
[distant alarms blaring]
- [sighs]
[pensive music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, here you go.
[sniffles]
They had the almonds
that you like, too,
so I got them for you.
Am I interrupting anything?
You need to make
a phone call or something?
- I'll tell you
if you're interrupting.
Buckle up.
- Yes, sir.
- My husband got catfished
into robbing a bank
for an imaginary girl he thinks
he's cheating on me with?
- Yes.
- I mean,
it's not a perfect marriage,
but I thought we were happy.
- This is an awful situation.
- What am I supposed to do now?
- Well, if I were you,
I'd file for divorce
and change the locks.
- Yeah, I think I will.
Thank you.
- Oof.
[vehicle approaching]
[suspenseful music]
- There's Reggie.
♪ ♪
- Trip to the hardware store--
ultimate red flag.
- And that shovel is proving
my theory that he buried
the diamonds in the desert.
You know, we stay on him,
he'll lead us right to them.
You think Oscar's
got the same plan?
Figure he's watching right now?
- I think we should assume
he does and keep a low profile.
- Hey, buddy.
Yeesh.
Prison wasn't kind to you.
Well, well.
The gang's all here.
[elevator dings]
- [sighs]
- Hey.
- Hi.
- How'd you sleep?
- Uh, not well.
How have I never noticed
how noisy our apartment is
during the day?
Oh, this is cute.
- Oh, thank you.
- Yeah, Boot's got a date.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh.
- You got any advice for me?
- Well, what did Tim say?
- Well, he encouraged me
to keep my expectations low.
- Wow. Is it the first date?
- Yeah.
- Well, make the first date
all about her, you know?
Just listen more than you talk.
- All right.
Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
- Miles, can I
show you something?
It'll only take a minute.
[chuckles]
- Hey.
- Hi.
- I know you're
about to clock in,
but I'd love to find
some time to catch up.
- I'd like that.
- You're off Wednesday, right?
- Good morning, Sergeant.
The Dream Team is in the house.
Excited to hit the ground
running with you tonight.
We await your orders.
- Yeah.
Staying awake for one
would be great.
Sorry, I gotta go.
- Okay, but what about
Wednesday?
- Oh, yeah, right.
Um, yeah, I'm in.
[mellow music]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
- Miles?
- Rina.
- Hi.
- Hey. It's nice to meet you.
- It's so nice to meet you.
- Uh, may I?
- Oh.
Wow. Thank you.
A real restaurant on a first
date, and he's a gentleman.
- [chuckles]
Well, what can I say?
It's the way my mama raised me.
- Can I get you guys started
with something to drink?
- Can you recommend a red wine?
- Well, the Bordeaux blend
is very nice.
- Okay, I'll do a glass.
Or should we do a bottle?
- Yeah. Yeah, sure.
Whatever the lady wants.
- Thank you.
[phone keyboard clacking]
- You look--you look great,
by the way.
- You're not too bad yourself,
although I was kind of hoping
you'd be wearing the uniform.
- Oh, no.
I keep that at the station.
- Mm. What about your gun?
[cork pops]
Oh, thank you.
[phone keyboard clacking]
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Sorry.
It's my brother.
He likes to check up on me.
- Oh, no worries.
Are y'all close?
- Yeah.
Nothing more important
than family.
- To family.
- Yeah.
Cheers.
- Cheers.
[tense music]
- So how long have you been
working for the LAPD?
What station
do you work out of?
- Uh, a few months.
I'm a rookie.
- Oh, okay. Yeah.
- I'm gonna--
I'm gonna run to the bathroom
right quick.
I'll be right back.
- Okay.
♪ ♪
- I don't know.
Maybe I'm overreacting.
Seven might just be
her lucky number.
- In numerology,
seven is very important.
It represents wisdom,
intuition, mystery.
- Yeah, well, the Eastern Front
uses it as a symbol of power.
- Yeah, and they have
a hate-on for the LAPD
because we put half
their leadership in jail
after they attacked Del Monte.
You want me to run her?
What's her name?
- Rina Davitt.
You know, maybe I'm
overreacting because of the,
you know, the catfish case.
- Or maybe you think
something's off because it is.
Look, I'm gonna run her.
If it gets flagged,
we'll just explain
that your date
acted suspiciously.
- All right, all right.
- How's Rina getting him
back here?
- She's gonna ask him
to walk her to her car.
And when she does, we stomp him
and throw him in the trunk.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- You're in trouble.
- I'm in trouble.
- Rina's brother is
in the Eastern Front.
You gotta get out of there.
- To the front! Go!
- Hey, what's going on?
- I gotta go.
- No, stay! Stay!
[crowd murmuring]
- Go! Go! Get him!
- There he is!
- Come on!
- LAPD! I need your vehicle!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, stop.
- Get down!
[gunfire]
[glass shattering]
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
[engine turns over]
- Go! Car!
[tires squealing,
engine revving]
[phone ringing]
- Hey.
Aren't you supposed
to be sleeping?
- Miles is in trouble.
Eastern Front going after him
at Table and Thyme.
[siren wailing]
[engines roaring]
- ♪ I spit venom ♪
[gunshots]
[beeping]
- 911, what's your emergency?
- This is Officer Miles Penn!
Badge number 653013.
I'm being pursued by armed
suspects, taking heavy fire.
[siren wailing]
- ♪ I spit venom ♪
- Hey!
We've got an officer
in trouble.
Get your asses into gear now!
- ♪ Check it out ♪
♪ ♪
- Control,
attach Adam-50, Adam-44,
Adam-46, Adam-55 to my call.
- Copy, Lincoln-300.
[phone rings]
- Please tell me
the cavalry's coming!
- Code 3, where are you?
- Van Nuys heading south.
- Make a right
at the next corner
and head for
the overlook parking lot.
We gotta intercept these guys
where it's safe for civilians.
Bring the chase to us.
- Yes, ma'am.
Come on, come on, come on.
[tires squealing]
- ♪ I spit venom,
venom, venom ♪
- [yells]
[gunfire]
[glass shatters]
- ♪ I spit venom ♪
[gunfire]
[tires squealing]
- We got him trapped!
[sirens wailing]
- ♪ Check it out ♪
♪ I spit venom ♪
- Drivers,
turn your engines off
and throw the keys
out the window!
Then step out.
All of you,
get out of your cars.
Slowly, with your hands
in the air.
Let's go.
Control, we're Code 4.
We've got five suspects
in custody.
- Sergeant, you and your squad
totally saved my bacon.
- Yeah, they did good.
Sorry your date turned out
to be such a nightmare.
- Thanks.
You know, I think I'm gonna
embrace the single life
for a little bit longer.
- Yeah. I hear that.
[animal howling]
[phone buzzes]
- What are you
doing up so late?
- I'm worrying about my man.
Any sign of Oscar?
- [yawning]
Not yet.
- You sound tired.
- I'm okay.
Just been staring at the same
door for the last three hours.
I figure Reggie's
gonna slip out at dawn
and go dig up the diamonds
he buried.
- Can't Harper
give you a break?
- I didn't wanna
wake her up just yet.
I got the feeling that
she was looking forward
to some uninterrupted sleep.
- You're a good man,
John Nolan.
- I try.
- All right, well,
I just wanted to check in.
I'll let you get back to it.
Maybe you should
find some caffeine.
- Yeah, that's not a bad idea.
All right. Love you.
- I love you too.
[animal howling]
- [sighs]
[device beeps]
[ominous music]
[Taser crackling]
[groaning]
♪ ♪
[groans]
- Oh, John.
This stuff will kill you.
[can pops open]
♪ ♪
[Pat Benatar's "Hit Me
With Your Best Shot" playing]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Well, you're a real
tough cookie ♪
♪ With a long history ♪
♪ Of breaking little hearts
like the one in me ♪
♪ That's okay,
let's see how you do it ♪
♪ Put up your dukes,
let's get down to it ♪
♪ Hit me with your best shot ♪
♪ Come on, hit me
with your best shot ♪
♪ Hit me with your best shot ♪
♪ Fire away ♪
[banging]
John, the driver gets
to pick the music.
You know this.
Besides, Pat Benatar
is a national treasure,
which is really fitting
because, you know,
we're on a treasure hunt
right now.
Well, technically, I'm
embarking on a treasure hunt.
For you, the pot of gold
at the end of the rainbow
is a shallow grave.
- ♪ Hit me with
your best shot ♪
- ♪ Hit me
with your best shot ♪
♪ Fire away ♪
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
[sighs]
Damn it, Nolan.
You were supposed
to wake me up.
[sighs]
[line rings]
[drone whirring]
Hey, drone kid.
You seen the guy
I was with yesterday?
- The cop?
- Yeah.
- No.
- Hmm.
[phone buzzing]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
This is Detective
Nyla Harper, LAPD.
I have a possible
officer in jeopardy.
Sunrise Motel.
- Hey, lady cop.
Look at this.
♪ ♪
- Man!
You forget how clean the air is
when you're bouncing around
city to city.
[sighs]
You ever been
to Big Sky Country, John?
Oh, I've always wanted to go.
You know...
[grunts]
Maybe I'll buy myself a ranch
with all this diamond money.
Okay, John,
I'm gonna open the trunk.
Any sudden moves,
and I'm going to shoot you.
Do you understand?
- I understand.
- Great.
So nice to work
with professionals.
[beeping]
[trunk creaks]
There he is.
Climb out.
- [grunts]
- I'd offer to help you,
but I'm not an idiot.
I know that even
with those chains on,
you're one dangerous hombre.
- Where's Reggie?
- Oh, I didn't
need him anymore.
- He told you where
the diamonds are hidden?
- No, even better.
He had the map
tattooed on his arm.
- God.
- [laughs]
He didn't even
tell me at first.
He let me torture him
for a while.
And then all of a sudden,
I was like,
hey, what's that on your arm?
Once I had the map,
I didn't really need him
since I had you in the trunk.
- You know, you could have just
taken a photo of the tattoo.
- Mm.
I didn't even think of that.
Here, hold it up.
This is the problem with
being institutionalized
half my life, John.
My default is
to just go full caveman.
[camera shutter clicks]
That's good.
Okay.
- Now what?
- Uh, chuck it.
- Just--
- Yep.
Now we're gonna go on
a hike for some treasure.
And then you're gonna
dig it up for me.
Doesn't that sound like fun?
- Why don't you dig it up?
- It turns out
prison is bad for the back.
- Oscar took Nolan.
He has to be going
for the diamonds.
Local police are on the way,
but the search area is massive.
[tense music]
I need the world out here.
Feds, marshals,
anyone with a badge or a gun--
I need them looking for Nolan.
Okay.
Excuse me. I need your son.
- Sorry?
- I am a cop.
My partner was just abducted.
I need your son and his drone
to help me find him.
- What?
- Cool.
- No.
- Please.
I promise he won't be
in any danger.
I will protect him
with my life.
- Come on, Mom.
You're always talking about
doing the right thing.
This is it.
- [sighs]
You promise he'll be safe?
- 100%.
- [sighs]
Okay.
♪ ♪
- Thank you.
[hawk calling]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- All right.
I need eyes in the air.
- You got it.
[drone whirring]
- Anything?
- Just a lot of desert.
- Come on, John.
Where are you?
- You know,
it really warmed my heart
to see you at the motel
last night.
[chuckles]
I know it sounds crazy.
You're a cop,
and I'm a criminal.
But ours is the most stable
relationship I've ever had.
- That is truly sad.
- Yeah, you're telling me.
- Well, since we're BFFs now,
you mind telling me
how you and Jason managed
to escape from prison?
- That was Monica.
Yeah, she needed
some prison intel.
I leveraged an exit package.
But before you ask me,
I have no idea where she is.
But I know she's
onto something big.
Um, I'm having trouble
figuring out--no.
[bird cawing]
I can't tell
if this is a N or a W
or an M.
What does that look like
to you?
- It's a W.
And that line going up
toward the index finger,
that would be the dry river bed
we passed ten minutes ago.
- Damn it, I missed it.
Well, I guess
we'll turn around.
[drone whirring]
- Wait, I think I see a--
I think that's a person.
- That's a cactus.
- No, that's definitely--
that's a--that's a cactus.
- They could be anywhere.
- Wait, I saw a flash.
It's from a car window.
[tense music]
[drone whirring]
- Yes, that's them.
[engine revving]
- [panting]
♪ ♪
Here it is.
- How can you be so sure?
Huh.
I didn't expect it
to be so literal.
[clears throat]
♪ ♪
Get digging.
- It's gonna be
a little hard to dig
while I'm cuffed
like this, Oscar.
- Well, that's a real
sad face emoji, John.
Maybe if I blew off a few toes,
how much harder would that
make the digging?
- [grunts]
- Any footprints?
- No. I don't know.
Maybe we should have
headed south from the car.
- Let me see.
You know, I'd head up
further right, up the canyon.
[drone whirring]
Yes, there. That is them.
- Come on, chop, chop.
I'm on a schedule.
Come on.
[metallic clank]
Oh, that's the sweet clank
of success.
Come on, dig it out.
- [grunts]
- That's it.
Open it up.
Ah.
Open the second one.
[laughs]
Oh, mama.
There's more in there
than I thought there was.
Shut the box, John.
[tense music]
John, don't mistake
our relationship status
for compassion.
- Is he about
to shoot your partner?
- I can hurt you a lot
before I kill you.
Then I'll go after your wife.
- Yes, he is.
Hit him with the drone.
- What?
- Or I can just do it quick
and painless and leave her be.
Shut the damn box.
- Fly the drone into Oscar
as hard as you can.
- Am I gonna get
in trouble for this?
- No, you are gonna
be a hero.
Now, hit him with
the damn drone.
[drone whirring]
- Whoa!
[both grunting]
[coughs and grunts]
- Looks like my ride's here.
[helicopter whirring]
- So is mine!
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
- Get down in the footwell.
- Oh, okay!
[helicopter whirring]
[gunfire]
[glass shatters]
Oh, my God! Oh, no.
[bullets ricocheting]
Oh! Oh, no. Oh, no.
♪ ♪
Oh, no.
- Go! Go now!
♪ ♪
[gunshots]
Damn it!
♪ ♪
- Damn it.
[panting]
[sighs]
Oh, boy.
That drone strike saved my ass.
Was that you?
- No, that was the kid.
[debris clinks]
- Is it safe?
- Yeah.
You okay?
- All good.
- Nice flying, kid.
I owe you one.
- Don't worry about it.
This is killer footage.
- Huh, wow.
There's always
a silver lining for someone.
Bright side for us,
Oscar left empty-handed.
♪ ♪
- Can I--can I have one?
- Hi, Heidi.
Thanks for coming back in.
I just had a few follow-up
questions about your husband.
- Yeah, of course.
- I'll try to have you out
of here as quick as possible.
- Whatever you need.
I'm just ready to put this
all behind me.
- Perfectly understandable.
Have you seen
any suspicious activity
around your home lately?
Any break-in attempts,
strangers on your property,
missing laptops or devices?
- No, nothing like that.
I mean, it's just me at home
with two toddlers all day,
so if anything fishy happened,
I'd probably find it exciting.
- I hear that.
How much do you know
about IP addresses?
- Nothing.
- Me neither.
But according
to the nerds upstairs,
Boyana's messages to Julius
weren't coming
from Eastern Europe.
They were coming
from your house.
- What?
- I know. Crazy, right?
But if no one else had access
and Julius
didn't catfish himself,
that leaves one suspect.
You.
[tense music]
- I didn't mean for
any of this to happen.
My husband has
always been gullible.
And at first,
I found it endearing.
But over the past
several years,
I--it started driving me crazy.
All I could think about
was divorce,
but splitting everything
50/50 isn't fair
after all I put up with.
I just wanted what was mine.
- So you thought he'd empty
your savings account
to pay for Boyana's
heart operation,
then you'd be able
to hide the money
he sent you during the divorce.
- And instead, he went
and robbed a bank for her!
I mean, he can't even remember
to go and pick up milk
when I ask,
but for Boyana,
he's willing to risk prison?
[scoffs]
- Catfished by his own wife,
in his own home.
The amount of work that took
on both their parts,
I mean, can you imagine if they
had just focused their energy
on fixing their relationship?
You know, maybe now's
a good time to confirm
you're not hiding anything
from me, right?
- Don't be silly.
And I know you're not
hiding anything from me.
- That is correct.
- Mm-hmm.
- But maybe we should take
this cautionary tale
as a sign to, I don't know,
reconnect as a couple?
- Hmm.
How about a weekend reset?
- Hey.
Garza just called.
A high-priority meeting
is taking place
first thing in the morning
at Homeland Security.
He's asking for us to be there.
[The Marias' "Real Life"]
[soft upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Hello.
- Hi.
I know I'm exhausted to
the point of hallucination,
but you are not my roommate.
- [chuckles]
Celina let me in
before she left for work.
- Oh.
- Look, I know being
the supervising sergeant
on night shift can be rough,
so I got all your favorites.
- Pancakes,
chocolate croissant.
Are those veggie burgers?
- Oh, yeah.
Oh, we got a sea bass
warming in the oven too.
- This is perfect.
I mean, I'm not gonna
have to cook for a week.
- Well, look, go relax.
Let me finish up here.
♪ ♪
Hey, so listen, I've--
I've been doing
a lot of thinking
over the last few months...
- Okay.
- As we've been doing
whatever it is
that we're doing,
you know, the hookups,
the conversations about
what might happen
after you make sergeant.
And now that we're here,
I just--
I want you to know
that I would never assume
anything about our future.
- Mm.
- I know the damage I did.
And after a lot of therapy,
I know why I did it.
And I--look,
I've been doing the work.
I have.
I've been doing the work to fix
what's been broken inside me.
So you can trust me
when I tell you, Lucy,
I will never hurt you
like that again.
If we're gonna
get back together,
I think we should
take the next step,
and you should move in with me.
So we can give us a--
A real shot.
- ♪ Real life ♪
♪ Ooh, baby, yeah,
in real life ♪
- That was a good try.
- ♪ Can't stand another
whi-i-i-i-i-ite lie ♪
♪ And another
go-o-o-o-o-oodbye ♪
- To be continued.
- ♪ Go-o-o-o-o-oodbye ♪
[indistinct chatter]
- What the hell
are we walking into?
- Nolan.
I didn't know you
would be here.
- Yeah, um, Garza called me,
said he needed me.
I thought he wanted
an update on Oscar.
State police found the chopper
that he used to escape.
The pilot and door gunner
were both dead,
clearly, because Oscar
couldn't afford
to pay them for the rescue.
But I'm seeing you're here,
and all these bigwigs are here.
Something else is clearly
going on, isn't it?
- Yeah, but I don't know what.
- Thanks for coming.
Let me start by saying
what I'm about to tell you
was no one's first choice.
- Strong start.
- Well, the decision was made
at the top of the food chain.
Now, the entire
intelligence community
and Justice Department
agencies came together
to evaluate the intel
and the national security
repercussions of it being
released into the world.
- What intel?
- I can't tell you,
only that it is
beyond top secret
national intelligence,
including sources and methods.
- Okay, I'm sorry.
Am I the only one who's
deeply confused right now?
- No.
- Simply put,
the U.S. government
has been leveraged
using secrets stolen
from what we thought
was a secure NSA facility
here in Los Angeles.
- Leveraged by who?
- Wait. No.
- Yes.
Now, given the risk
to national security
if these secrets
were to be released,
we had no choice but
to make an immunity deal.
Now, believe me,
I pointed out all the ways
that this could backfire,
but I was overruled.
- An immunity deal with who?
[heels clicking]
[tense music]
- Monica.
- Miss me?
♪ ♪