DIPPER: Ah! Summer break!
- So do you want cheese on that, hon?
- WOMAN: Sure, Hank!
A time for leisure,
recreation and taking her easy.
Unless you're me.
(YELLING)
(SCREAMING)
(CREATURE GROWLING)
It's getting closer!
(GROWLING)
My name is Dipper.
The girl about to puke
is my sister Mabel.
You may be wondering
what we're doing in a golf cart,
fleeing from a creature
of unimaginable horror.
- Look out!
- Ah!
(BOTH YELLING)
Rest assured,
there's a perfectly logical explanation.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
DIPPER: Let's rewind.
It all began when our parents decided
we could use some fresh air.
They shipped us up North to a sleepy
town called Gravity Falls, Oregon,
to stay at our great uncle's place
in the woods.
This attic is amazing!
Check out all my splinters!
(BLEATING)
And there's a goat on my bed.
Hey, friend.
Oh! Yes, you can keep chewing
on my sweater!
(LAUGHING)
My sister tended
to look on the bright side of things.
Yay!
Grass!
But I was having a hard time
getting used to our new surroundings.
- Boo!
-(SCREAMS)
(GUFFAWING)
And then there was
our Great Uncle Stan. That guy.
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
(COUGHING)
It was worth it!
Our uncle had transformed his house
into a tourist trap
he called the Mystery Shack.
The real mystery
was why anyone came.
Ladies and gentlemen,
behold the Sascrotch!
(ALL EXCLAIM EXCITEDLY)
And guess who had to work there.
-(DIPPER SIGHS)
- Oh!
No touching the merchandise!
It looked like it was gonna be the same,
boring routine all summer.
Until one fateful day...
He's looking at it. He's looking at it!
Uh...
(READING)
- I rigged it!
- DIPPER: Mabel?
I know you're going through
your whole boy-crazy phase,
but I think you're kind of overdoing it
with the crazy part.
What? (BLOWS RASPBERRY)
Come on, Dipper!
This is our first summer
away from home.
It's my big chance
to have an epic summer romance!
Yeah, but do you need to flirt
with every guy you meet?
My name is Mabel. But you can call me
the girl of your dreams!
I'm joking!
(LAUGHING)
Oh, my gosh, you like turtles?
I like turtles, too!
What is happening here?
Come one, come all, to the Mattress
Prince's Kingdom of savings!
-(WHISPERS) Take me with you!
-(SCREAMS)
Mock all you want, brother,
but I got a good feeling
about this summer.
I wouldn't be surprised
if the man of my dreams
walked through that door right now!
(BELCHING)
Oh! Oh! Not good! Ow.
- Oh, why?
-(LAUGHING)
All right, all right. Look alive, people!
I need someone to go
hammer up these signs
in the spooky part of the forest.
- Not it!
Also not it.
Nobody asked you, Soos.
I know. And I'm comfortable with that.
Wendy, I need you to put up this sign.
I would, but I, uh, can't, uh, reach it.
I'd fire all of you if I could.
All right, let's make it,
eeny-meeny-miny... You!
Oh, what?
Grunkle Stan, whenever I'm in those
woods I feel like I'm being watched.
Ah, this again.
I'm telling you, something weird
is going on in this town.
Just today, my mosquito bite
spelled out "beware."
That says "bewarb."
Look, kid, the whole "monsters
in the forest" thing is just local legend,
drummed up by guys like me,
to sell merch to guys like that.
(LAUGHING)
So quit being so paranoid!
(SIGHS)
(WIND WHISTLING)
Ugh. Grunkle Stan...
Nobody ever believes anything I say.
-(METALLIC CLANK)
- Huh?
(CLANKING CONTINUES)
(HINGES CREAK)
-(MACHINERY WHIRRING)
-(BLEATING)
What the...
"It's hard to believe
it's been six years since I began
"studying the strange and wondrous
secrets of Gravity Falls, Oregon."
What is all this?
"Unfortunately, my suspicions have
been confirmed. I'm being watched.
"I must hide this book before he finds it.
"Remember, in Gravity Falls,
there is no one you can trust."
No one you can trust.
- Hello!
-(YELLS)
What you reading, some nerd thing?
Uh, uh... It's nothing!
(MOCKING) "Uh, uh. It's nothing!"
(LAUGHING) What, are you
actually not gonna show me?
Uh...
Let's go somewhere private.
It's amazing!
Grunkle Stan said I was being paranoid,
but according to this book,
Gravity Falls has this secret dark side.
Whoa!
Shut up!
And get this. After a certain point,
the pages just stop.
Like the guy who was writing it
mysteriously disappeared.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
- Who's that?
- Well, time to spill the beans!
Beans. This girl's got a date.
(HOOTS)
Let me get this straight.
In the half hour I was gone,
you already found a boyfriend?
What can I say?
I guess I'm just irresistible!
-(DOORBELL RINGING)
- Oh! Coming!
What you reading there, slick?
Oh'. 1 was just catching up on...
Gold Chains for Old Men Magazine?
That's a good issue.
Hey, family!
Say hello to my new boyfriend!
'SUP-
- Hey.
- How's it hanging?
We met at the cemetery.
He's really deep.
Oh! Little muscle there. That's...
What a surprise.
So, what's your name?
Uh...
Normal... Man!
He means Norman.
Are you bleeding, Norman?
(DRIPPING)
It's jam.
I love jam! Look at this!
So, you wanna go,
hold hands or whatever?
Oh, my goodness.
(GIGGLES) Don't wait up!
(CRASHING)
DIPPER: There was something
about Norman that wasn't right.
I decided to consult the journal.
"Known for their pale skin
and bad attitudes,
"these creatures
are often mistaken for teenagers!
"Beware Gravity Falls' nefarious..."
-(GASPS)
-(THUNDER CRASHES)
'SUP-
Zombie!
(ECHOING)
Did someone say, "Crombie"?
What is that? Crombie.
It's not even a word.
You're losing your mind.
(GRUNTING)
I like you.
Oh, no! Mabel!
No, no! Mabel, watch out!
Daisies? You scallywag!
Is my sister really dating a zombie?
Or am I just going nuts?
It's a dilemma to be sure.
I couldn't help but overhear you talking
aloud to yourself in this empty room.
Soos, you've seen Mabel's boyfriend.
He's gotta be a zombie right?
Hmm. How many brains
did you see the guy eat?
Zero.
Look, dude, I believe you. I'm always
noticing weird stuff in this town.
Like the mailman?
Pretty sure that dude's a werewolf.
But you gotta have evidence.
Otherwise people are gonna think
you're a major league cuckoo-clock.
As always, Soos, you're right.
My wisdom is both a blessing,
and a curse.
STAN: Soos! The portable toilets
are clogged again!
I am needed elsewhere.
DIPPER: My sister could be in trouble.
It was time to get some evidence.
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
-(CRASH)
-(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(EXCLAIMS)
I'd seen enough.
Mabel! We've got to talk about Norman!
Isn't he the best? Check out this
giant smooch mark he gave me!
-(EXCLAIMS)
-(LAUGHS)
Gullible. It was just an accident
with the leaf blower.
Kissing practice!
Mmm.
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
Turn it off! Turn it off!
That was fun.
No, Mabel, listen! I'm trying to tell you
that Norman is not what he seems!
(GASPS) You think
he might be a vampire?
That would be so awesome!
Guess again, sister.
- Sha-bam!
- Ah!
Oh, wait. I'm sorry. Sha-bam!
A zombie? That is not funny, Dipper.
I'm not joking.
It all adds up, the bleeding, the limp.
He never blinks! Have you noticed that?
Maybe he's blinking
when you're blinking.
Mabel, remember what the book said
about Gravity Falls?
Trust no one!
Well, what about me, huh?
Why can't you trust me?
Beep-BOP!
Mabel! He's gonna eat your brain!
Dipper, listen to me.
Norman and I are going on a date
at 5:00,
and I'm gonna be adorable,
and he's gonna be dreamy.
And I'm not gonna let you ruin it
with one of your crazy conspiracies!
(SIGHS) What am I gonna do?
-(CLOCK owl. HOOTS)
-(DOORBELL RINGS)
Coming!
Hey, Norman. How do I look?
Shiny!
You always know what to say.
Soos is right.
I don't have any real evidence.
I guess I can be kind of paranoid
sometimes and... Wait, what?
(SCREAMS)
I was right! Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh!
Grunkle Stan! Grunkle Stan!
Grunkle Stan!
And here we have
rock-that-looks-like-a-face rock.
The rock that looks like a face.
Does it look like a rock?
- No, it looks like a face.
- Is it a face?
It's a rock that looks like a face!
Over here! Grunkle Stan!
For the fifth time, it's not an actual face!
(GRUNTS IN FRUSTRATION)
Finally, we're alone.
Yes. Alone!
Stan! Stan!
Wendy! Wendy, Wendy!
I need to borrow the golf cart
so I can save my sister from a zombie!
Try not to hit any pedestrians.
Dude, it's me. Soos.
This is for the zombies.
Thanks.
And this is in case you see a pifiata.
Uh, thanks?
Better safe than sorry!
Mabel, now that we've gotten to know
each other,
there's something I should tell you.
Oh, Norman. You can tell me anything.
(THINKING) Please be a vampire!
Please be a vampire!
All right, just don't freak out, okay?
Just keep an open mind. Be cool.
Is this weird? Is this too weird?
You need to sit down?
All right. I'll explain. So, we're gnomes.
First off, get that one out of the way.
Uh...
I'm Jeff. And here we have Carson,
Steve, Jason and...
I'm sorry, I always forget your name.
Shmebulock.
Shmebulock, yes! Anyways.
Long story short, us gnomes
have been looking for a new queen.
Right, guys?
(TOGETHER) Queen, queen!
Ha. So what do you say?
Will you join us, in holy matrinomy.
Matri... Matrimony! Blah!
Can't talk today.
Look, I'm sorry, guys.
You're really sweet, but I'm a girl.
And you're gnomes. And it's like, what?
Yikes!
We understand.
We'll never forget you, Mabel.
Because we're gonna kidnap you.
- Huh?
-(YELLING)
(SCREAMING)
Don't worry, Mabel!
I'll save you from that zombie!
MABEL: Help!
Hold on!
The more you struggle,
the more awkward
this is gonna be for everybody!
Just... Okay!
Just get her arm there, Steve.
Hey, let go of me!
(GROANS)
What the heck is going on here?
(HISSES)
Dipper! Norman turned out to be
a bunch of gnomes!
And they're total jerks! Hair! Hair! Hair!
Gnomes? I was way off.
"Gnomes.
Little men of the Gravity Falls forest.
"Weaknesses, Unknown."
Oh, come on!
Hey, hey! Let go of my sister!
Oh. (LAUGHS)
Hey, there! Um, you know, this is all
really just a big misunderstanding.
You see, your sister's not in danger.
She's just marrying
all one thousand of us
and becoming our gnome queen
for all eternity.
Isn't that right, honey?
You guys are butt-faces!
Give her back right now, or else!
You think you can stop us, boy?
You have no idea what we're capable of.
The gnomes are a powerful race!
Do not trifle with the...
(YELLS)
He's getting away with our queen!
No, no, no!
Seatbelt.
You've messed
with the wrong creatures, boy.
Gnomes of the forest, assemble!
Hurry before they come after us!
I wouldn't worry about it.
Did you see their little legs?
The suckers are tiny!
-(LOUD STOMPING)
-(BRAKES SCREECHING)
Dang.
All right, teamwork, guys.
Like we practiced!
(ROARING)
Move, move!
Come back with our queen!
It's getting closer!
-(HORN HONKS)
- Shmebulock...
I'll save you, Dipper!
- Thanks, Mabel!
- Don't mention it.
Look out!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(BOTH GROANING)
Stay back, man!
(ROARING)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Where's Grunkle Stan?
Behold...
The world's most distracting object!
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
Just try to look away, you can't!
I can't even remember
what I was talking about.
JEFF: It's the end of the line, kids!
Mabel, marry us
before we do something crazy!
There's gotta be a way out of this.
I gotta do it.
What? Mabel!
Don't do this! Are you crazy?
- Trust me.
- What?
Dipper, just this once, trust me.
All right, Jeff. I'll marry you.
Hot dog! Help me down there, Jason.
Thanks, Andy.
All right, left foot, there we go.
Watch those fingers, Mike.
Eh? Eh?
Bada-bing, bada-bam!
Now let's get
you back into the forest honey.
You may now kiss the bride.
Well! Don't mind if I do.
Hey, hey, wait a minute.
What's going on?
(SCREAMING)
That's for lying to me!
That's for breaking my heart!
Ow! My face!
And this is for messing with my brother!
(GROANS)
- Wanna do the honors?
- On three!
- One! Two! Three!
(SCREAMING) I'll get you back for this!
(ALL SCREAMING)
Who's giving orders? I need orders!
My arms are tired.
Anyone else wants some?
(WHIMPERING)
(BLEATING)
(GNOME SCREAMING)
Hey, Dipper,
I'm sorry for ignoring your advice.
You really were just looking out for me.
Oh, don't be like that.
You saved our butts back there!
I guess I'm just sad
that my first boyfriend turned out
to be a bunch of gnomes.
Look on the bright side.
Maybe the next one will be a vampire.
Oh! You're just saying that!
Awkward sibling hug?
Awkward sibling hug.
- Pat. Pat.
(ENTRY BELL RINGS)
Sheesh! You two get hit
by a bus or something? Ha!
Hey! Wouldn't you know it?
I accidentally overstocked
some inventory,
so, how's about you each take one item
from the gift shop,
on the house, you know?
- Really?
- What's the catch?
That catch is do it before I change
my mind. Now take something.
- Hmm...
- Ooh! (CHUCKLES)
Hmm.
That ought to do the trick!
And I will have a grappling hook!
Yes!
Wouldn't you rather have,
like, a doll or something?
Grappling hook!
Fair enough!
DIPPER: This journal told me there
was no one in Gravity Falls I could trust.
But when you battle a hundred
gnomes side by side with someone,
you realize that they've probably
always got your back.
Hey, Mabel, could you get the light?
I'm on it.
It worked!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Grappling hook.
DIPPER: Our uncle told us there was
nothing strange about this town.
But who knows what other secrets
are waiting to be unlocked?
(GROANS)
Who are the real-world Illuminati ?
Find out @ saveanilluminati.com