It's game day here,
round two of the U.S. Open.
We've got Valiente
taking on La Fe.
As always, Valiente is one of
the favorites here to win the U.S. Open.
La Fe is definitely
gonna have their hands full today,
going up against the GOAT,
Adolfo Cambiaso.
La Fe is a very young organization.
They've only been playing together
for a few years.
Where the fuck is Louis?
If Cambiaso is standing back,
let's have a bit of patience to attack.
Okay.
Notice that from
where we started having it,
he started getting in.
- Once he gets in…
- Then yes.
Then yes, we go there.
- Let's play where it's not his area.
- Okay.
Damn him.
Fuck.
- How you doing? I'm good.
- How are you, officer?
I'm Deputy Ficarra
with the Sheriff's Office.
The reason I'm pulling you over,
you were up at 57. That's a 40 back there.
- I'm so sorry.
- I know.
Anything to say?
We're playing against
Cambiaso and we got stopped by the police.
You're such an asshole, dude.
I'll write the citation.
The options are listed here on the back.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Is there anything to add?
We're coming. We're coming.
We're playing against Cambiaso
when we get there.
Being late,
that pisses me the fuck off, man.
We're driving as fast as possible.
We're hoping I was going to get there
before the game started going.
In this sport,
you need so many things to be perfect.
Showing up five minutes before a game,
I was embarrassed.
I was so pissed.
They called Robi.
We're now playing against Cambiaso.
Unlucky for him, though, we're here.
Adolfo Cambiaso,
he's the best player that's ever lived.
And he's got the best organization
with the best horses.
But in that moment,
I really don't care about all that.
About motherfucking time.
Big fucking game.
With our new offensive strategy,
we're gonna beat 'em.
We're gonna fuck this motherfucker up.
La Fe headed towards
the scoreboard.
Valiente headed towards
the Alan Carroll side.
Both teams getting lined up
for this first throw-in.
Ball is bowled in. First ball of the day
going to pop out towards the La Fe side.
Here comes Adolfo Cambiaso.
We've got
a good strategy going in,
which was for me to be more
of an offensive force
when we recouped the ball.
Elizalde gets there,
steals it back for La Fe.
Hits the ball forward, looking forward.
Devaleix, Louis is going to get there.
Come on, Louis.
Louis leaves it behind there.
Oh. Yikes.
Stolen back by Cambiaso.
Adolfo fires a beautiful pass
up to Paquito.
Paquito is alone at the front.
Louis cutting across
center field, trying to catch him here.
Paquito shoots, knocked down by Elizalde.
Look at that, but Peke Gonzalez is there.
And that one finally
went on through the goal.
You can tell
he's a little overwhelmed and nervous.
He's, like, trying to kill the ball.
He just needs to keep his calm.
Ball is back in play.
Adolfo Cambiaso winds up, shoots to goal.
It is on through the uprights.
Perfectly done there by Cambiaso.
Motherfucker.
If you don't try to build a lead
against Cambiaso, you're fucked.
Cambiaso's takeoff to goal
on a breakaway. Oh my goodness.
Cambiaso puts it on through the uprights.
Back-to-back goals there from the GOAT.
Goal number four.
De Narvaez gets it done.
Paco drills it straight on through here.
What a goal. What a horse.
Fran leaves it for Devaleix…
Come on.
In for the red zone…
That's a goal. Fantastic.
Well done, Louis and Fran.
Paco, right down the middle.
6-2, now the score.
They started goal, goal, goal.
It kind of brought us
back down to reality.
That will do it
for the first half.
We get a quick five-minute halftime.
Our team's strategy was… short-lived
when… it goes back to fucking Cambiaso.
Five minutes,
he knows exactly what we're gonna do
the next three chukkers.
He comes to me,
but many times he goes to a pass.
That's when I leave it to you.
- I'm leaving you the six-goaler, there.
- No. It works fine.
We get organized.
Sorry, we missed a goal
right in front of them.
You are the king of
the penalty and the goal here.
Let's see, now they are putting it wrong.
Valiente doubling
up La Fe on the scoreboard.
I'll hit you guys with a few announcements
while we wait. Just a reminder…
- It's close.
- We've got lots of polo left.
I'm feeling good.
And coming from a pregnant lady,
that means I'm feeling great.
This season is different
than it has been in the past.
I'm not playing at all,
but I can go watch polo.
If I were me circa five years ago,
I wouldn't have time
to be here doing this, supporting him.
- I'm going… stir-crazy.
It's okay.
I mean, like, not managing a house.
Of course. But it's
very difficult not working like I was,
not playing like I was playing,
and having those two elements
kind of taken out of my life
because now I feel very stagnant,
and I'm not a person
who enjoys a stagnant lifestyle.
- What brings me joy is the hustle.
- Yeah.
I am a polo player
and an attorney in Chicago
at a law firm there and working remotely.
Because I'm pregnant
with a baby girl, everything else
kind of just became second priority.
I'm happy to be the sweet pregnant wife
supporting her husband
for a period of time,
but that is not who I've been
or what I have strived for.
So…
Both teams line back up
at center field. Ball's in play.
Devaleix with the pickup right here.
Louis Devaleix going to the goal.
Come on, Louis.
Good job, Louis.
Ooh,
leaves that one behind, though.
Louis.
We had one strategy going into it.
We started getting killed
and didn't pivot to another strategy.
Louis on the run to goal.
Paquito to the inner vice,
trying to get the hook.
Louis's ball spits out to the left side,
and crosses that back line wide.
Fuck!
When it ends,
I'd be careful coming into the tent.
Gonzalez gets away from Diaz.
He's in the red zone.
Peke Gonzalez shoots and scores.
Final horn sounds.
Valiente comes out victorious.
I mean, I get it,
losing against a good team,
but not getting killed
the way we just got fucking killed.
How do I feel
about our performance? Um…
Angry.
Um, pissed off.
Uh… highly disappointed.
No, no, no, it can't be.
It's not possible that we keep losing.
After that loss,
we knew we had to win
the next game, otherwise we're out.
Devastating loss for La Fe.
Valiente moves to a 2-0 record,
and now if La Fe loses their next game,
they are out of the U.S. Open.
After the game,
I went to the barn, got on three horses,
and hit penalty shots
and went stick and balling.
I'm super, super disappointed.
We can't play like that.
We have the best chemistry off the field,
but it's just not working.
I wanna blow the fucking team up.
We shouldn't have changed
the strategy. We played better last time.
I mean, you're playing against Cambiaso.
- Fuck him.
- He's Adolfo. He's Cambiaso. That's not a…
That's the best it's gonna be.
- The most difficult game you'll play.
- Okay.
And then Peke,
who's super talented
on really good horses, and Paco.
Hello?
I got a phone call
from Ames' school.
My son just got pulled
into the principal's office.
Okay, what happened?
Ames is six years old.
Being a father is the best thing
that can happen.
I've been blessed with Ames.
Getting that call,
I was sad for my kid.
Sad that he's probably scared
he got pulled in that day
to the principal's office.
And you apologize to everybody.
You understand?
Bye. Bye, my son.
The fuck.
We fucking lost and my kid's misbehaving.
A little bit disappointed in myself.
I have spent a lot of time away
from my son during the U.S. Open.
If I made him
my number one priority this season,
maybe this is something
he would not have done.
I'm just so mad.
And Ames today, getting in trouble.
It's just…
I'm starting to think about whether
it's worth it. You know?
Yeah.
Polo can take a toll on your family.
There are times where it's difficult.
But the best you can do
is support the people you love
and hope that, you know, it all works out.
I'm tired of spending all this money.
I just can't win.
Like, forget today ever happened.
This is a good opportunity for you
to take a look at what's not working
and for you to make
the changes you need to make.
Because you're good at doing that.
It didn't go. Make a wish one more time.
- I love you, babe.
- Love you.
This lake looks pretty good.
When I'm too stressed
from the U.S. Open, I will go fishing.
Teams with chemistry, you feel like
you're with your friends playing
or having fun with your friends
all day long, playing in Coca-Cola.
We did it at a moment,
then Negro went down,
and Negro's thing was tough, I think.
It was really tough.
So, I mean, everything changes.
So, it is a strange season, you know.
Fishing requires a lot of patience
and it's the only thing
I have patience for, it's fishing, so.
I play polo for a living.
Since I remember,
I was really good friends
with Poroto Cambiaso.
We played together
since probably we were six or seven
until we were 14 for sure.
Won a couple
of very, uh, impressive tournaments.
Eighteen, yeah?
And he's already a six-goal player.
Two years ago, I was lucky to play
with Poroto and his dad.
With Poroto, it's amazing.
I mean, he's my age.
I don't know, from a year to another,
he made a huge jump. It's unreal.
As good as he is,
as young as he is, I'm wondering
if he doesn't put
added pressure on himself
to try to live up to Poroto too,
his friend, his buddy, you know?
Poroto's not really a fair comparison
because he's a freak of nature.
- When do you play? Against?
I don't know yet. With La Dolfina.
Oh. Tough team, yeah. They play amazing.
You always try to push yourself the most,
but you see yourself compared to the guys,
like Poroto, that are on the top now.
You're not far in a way, but really far
on some other ones, you know?
Those guys are improving every day
and they have a lot of help
with organization and everything.
So, I hope to be there.
I mean, I work for it every day.
It's what I dream,
but it's not really easy.
I really want to win
this competition.
I mean, to be 18, playing the U.S. Open,
and a team like Coca-Cola,
it's amazing. Really important for me.
Poroto is my friend
and I always respect him,
but to win, I need to beat La Dolfina.
In order to win this tournament,
I have to go through my friend, Poroto.
When I was born,
I was like a little bean.
That's why I'm Poroto.
When I was really, really young,
I knew I was going to be a polo player,
and I had the best teacher.
It's not easy to be Poroto
because he had to deal with all the stress
of being Adolfo's son.
The question was
if he was going to be able
to be as good as his father.
Adolfo Cambiaso was the youngest player
to ever go to 10 goals at age 19.
Then his son comes along
and beat his dad's record right there
to be the youngest player
to ever achieve a 10-goal handicap.
One week after his 17th birthday.
That's mind-boggling.
This is Poroto's
18-year-old version of himself.
It's a better version
than Adolfo's 18-year-old version,
which was at the time
beyond everybody's beliefs
what he could do
with the ball and his speed,
but in terms of gameplay,
Poroto is even better than his father.
- Are you the youngest 10-goaler?
- Yeah.
- In history? Can you tell me that?
- Mm.
I don't like to tell that.
Poroto is today top three,
four players in the world, I think.
He's a kid,
but inside the field, you don't feel it.
I mean,
that fucking kid Poroto is unbelievable.
It's just unbelievable.
And Panelo is unbelievable.
La Dolfina and the youth on that team,
uh, you know, it's amazing.
La Dolfina team is Poroto Cambiaso
and Tommy Panelo and Rufino Merlos.
And then of course Alejandro Aznar.
With the exception of Aznar,
I don't know if any of them can buy beer.
In this generation,
the speed, it's a whole different game.
Yes, there was passing before,
but the passing now
is just a whole nother level.
They are so in tune
with each other. They're not talking.
They're not calling. They just know.
I won the U.S. Open
once with my dad.
It was a really important moment for me.
It's a good opportunity to win
the most important tournament in America
without my dad.
- It's you playing in this tournament?
- Who?
- You?
- Yeah.
- You're not playing on this team?
No, on another team.
- We lost the final against Poroto.
Really?
- We beat him in the final before.
- Exactly.
In the 2024 Gauntlet of Polo,
Adolfo won the C.V. Whitney.
Poroto won the Gold Cup.
What really is special
about La Dolfina and Valiente
is that both those teams were
in our two finals leading up to the Open.
One on one. Let's see.
- We need to get there now.
- Yeah, right?
Action starting off heated
in the first two chukkers.
Both teams are looking for a way
to get out in front of the other.
Pieres, he's gonna leave it here
for Keko. Keko keeps it away.
No, gets it stolen away right here.
You see how far they reach?
Oh, yeah.
They're leaning all the way out.
They lean all the way out.
Come on!
Hey, I love it.
That one did get away from him.
Ooh, look. The two of them
having some words. I love it.
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. What's going on here?
We do see a yellow card
coming up here.
That can happen when
a dangerous and/or deliberate foul is made
going against Keko Magrini
on a dangerous use of the mallet.
This could be a devastating play
for Coca-Cola.
Does anybody talk shit
to each other when they play?
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah?
Good question.
Do you talk shit
to your son when you're playing?
No, I try not to.
If I need
to put a bit of pressure, you do.
- Yeah, of course.
- It's funny, you switch it on and off.
You go from being the guy's best friend…
- To…
- …to…
calling him everything you can imagine.
A lot of times things can get dangerous
just that quick.
They don't mean for it to get dangerous.
And so it heightens your…
frustration, sensitivity, whatever.
It makes sense.
Poroto
will take this attempt.
I think their second
goal shot penalty of the day. Cambiaso…
Oh, off the post.
A goal right here.
Aznar,
able to pick that one up.
Coca-Cola here playing
catch up in the second half
against the best team
in the gauntlet thus far.
Son of a bitch.
What a shame.
A good half, except for the end.
Keko's
having trouble finding his stride
in this game against this La Dolfina team.
Keko, I don't care if you get
a yellow card, but turn it around.
You started very well.
Hopefully he'll
do better in the second half.
The ball's back in play.
Keko, he connects to the center
where he finds Ruiz
who's still on, uh, Coppa Field.
Oh. Oh! Somebody's gonna be wrong here.
The play's under review
for a yellow card here,
which would be devastating
for Coca-Cola if they do,
because that'd make
Keko have to sit for two minutes,
ah, if they gave him a yellow.
Keko will sit
for two minutes
picking up his second yellow card
of the contest.
That is devastating.
Coke managed to claw their way back,
and then Keko picks up
his second yellow card,
forcing his team to play a man down.
It's a lot of emotions,
and you're really high up
and so much intensity
and everything that it's hard
for nothing to happen, you know?
Penalty two put on through
by Panelo.
Breaks a tie, takes back the lead
to make the score 11-10.
Coke's got some work to do right here.
Keko will be sitting
the remainder of this chukker,
and I believe 26 seconds
of the sixth chukker as well.
Shit.
They're calling me
for everything.
When it's four players
against three, it's a lot.
It's that you're more mad at yourself
that you're letting your team down.
Polito's gonna
take it back to the inside,
trying to burn up the time
as much as they can.
And still put one on the board here.
Polito, his shot is
over the back line. Wide.
We got a whistle sounding.
Looks like we're gonna get
a penalty two for Coca-Cola.
- Listen, that's what we needed right now.
- No, I know.
Getting some offense going
with just three players on the field.
Polito sends it on through.
Wow, look at this. Three on four,
and they're able to pick up a point
as Keko is stuck in the penalty box.
Polito Pieres,
the captain of the Coca-Cola team,
is able to tie up the game,
11 goals apiece on the board,
going into chukker number six.
Now we need to really just
make our comeback, like, big,
so we can have a good day.
It was a good chukker.
Come on, let's go.
One more. One more.
We've got Keko
back out on the field.
Coming in hot, it'll be Keko
to try to get to him. Look at this.
Panelo, got it!
These young guns are changing the game
right before our very eyes.
Many times the games
get decided on the last five minutes,
and you cannot relax for a second.
This kid is good.
Look at that, in the red zone,
Poroto Cambiaso!
Huge goal to go up two
with a couple minutes left.
Plenty of time for Coke.
Rufi, coming in, it's gonna
be Poroto on the near side here.
Can he get away from…
Now Keko picks it up again, Keko.
You don't have enough time.
Oh my goodness,
Keko let that one get away from him.
No way, oh my goodness, all right.
The wheels just fell off here for Coke.
Two quick goals by La Dolfina,
and then Rufi picks up this third one
to maybe just put it
out of reach right here.
- Game over?
Yeah.
Red zone here, yes, he does!
Oh my goodness,
tough break there for Keko.
I think so, that might
just get it done here for La Dolfina.
Keko can't keep control. A big one there.
It is all but over here.
What a tough loss for Coca-Cola.
What a game. La Dolfina team
continues to set the pace.
Big win here against Coca-Cola.
Keko is very young. Uh…
He needs to work
to play more with the men
and not too much with the ball.
I think the young kids nowadays,
they see Poroto Cambiaso,
and I think it's not good for polo.
Because they are something different.
It's not going to help their polo.
Keko is a fantastic handler
of the ball.
He's the guy that you want
normally to have the ball on your team
to go to goal,
unless you have
Polito Pieres on your team.
You can hold him up against Poroto,
Adolfo, against any other player.
He's right there with them in those terms.
So I think it's very difficult for Keko
to find his place really on that team.
With that win, La Dolfina
will move to the top of the standings
while Coca-Cola sinks to an 0-2 record.
It's a game that must be won.
They were playing for everything.
It was a difficult game for us.
I think we were a bit nervous,
especially me.
But, in the last chukker, I forgot
all the things that I was thinking,
and we all played good as a team,
and I think that's why we won.
Poroto, he's the future.
You're against him,
but you're happy for him.
- I've been with him since he…
- Since he was little.
- He's like my son.
- That's so cool.
Valiente and La Dolfina
are different teams,
but they're the same organization.
They are sister organizations, basically.
Under the same umbrella.
So they're coming out of the same barn,
but they're like this, you know?
Congratulations, Poroto.
Thanks!
Bob is like a second father.
Poroto's been playing a lot
of Bob's horses through all his career.
Everything we do is together.
Adolfo and Poroto,
these sister organizations,
they both have won a tournament.
They want to play each other, and I'm sure
they want to do it in the finals,
but in order to do that, they have to play
well enough to get to the semifinals
to have a chance
to play against each other.
That's not guaranteed at this point
because we've got a lot of good teams.
I want to win against my dad
so I can say that I beat
the greatest of the sport.
I felt the things were not going
really good my way.
I was just probably mad at myself
more than anything.
I played not good.
I think now it's more stressful
because of the future.
These players really
have to work hard to make a living.
They're bouncing around and they're always
trying to stay competitive,
trying to increase their skill
as to whether or not
they'll be picked up by a team.
So, if you have a bad year,
it can have
a detrimental effect on your career.
There's a lot of competition.
Everybody is fighting for themselves
to get a job, to improve.
It's a tough sport.
Hi!
Hi, guys. How are you
Are you gonna go over yonder later?
They'll come to the gallery.
My boyfriend's on his way.
So you have to come tonight.
During the winter season,
Wellington is really fun.
And there's always
something to do with your friends.
Keko is eat,
sleep, breathe polo.
It's his life,
it's his career, it's everything.
Mentally, you need a way to de-stress.
I try to, like, help him go out
and, like, not think about polo
for, like, an hour or two hours.
Oh, boy.
Pretend that you like me, okay.
But you know I do. Don't say pretend.
You know what I want to know?
How do you guys stay friends
when you compete with each other?
Like, everybody changes inside the field.
You're really mean when playing.
Screaming…
He's mean. He bullies me.
The things you say,
do you just get off the horse
and forget about all of it.
- There's never bad blood.
- If only girls could be like that.
You say one thing and then it's just gone.
It's really fun when we all go out.
The polo boys,
they're all friends with each other.
They all know each other.
Keko definitely has a large friend group.
The U.S. Open is
the most important tournament in the U.S.
that he plays, so it's intense.
I can see him relax,
have fun with his friends,
and have fun with me and my friends.
It's really nice for him.
But a night out in Wellington
is pretty short-lived.
It's very in-the-moment fun,
but then right back to work
for Keko the next day.
Son, you ready?
The helicopter?
Yeah, we're gonna go
pick up Yaya and Papu.
Pam's father can't sit in a car
for a long, extended period of time.
He's 86 years old
and had really serious cancer.
Have you ever been
on a helicopter like that?
Yes.
I've been watching Pam struggle
with the thought of not seeing her dad.
And it's a killer.
My dad and I are super close.
We have been my whole life.
My parents have come
to a few matches over the years,
and they always enjoy their time here.
But because of his health,
my dad hasn't been able to attend lately.
So it's really amazing
to get my dad out and get him
socializing with people I love.
Look at that.
That's where we're gonna play later today.
How cool is that?
- So cool.
- Yeah.
I lost my dad
and still to this day, it's tough for me.
So I just felt it was nice for Pam
to be able to watch a Sunday game
with her father, um, and her mother.
I have to give you chocolate cake.
- Is that cool?
Yeah.
Louis, how you doing, pal?
- Mr. Flanagan, how are you?
Want milk?
- Everything good?
A little better every day.
- You're looking good.
Yeah, I feel fine.
Louis,
you want a cup of coffee?
I would love a cup, Yaya. Thank you.
But you don't get
any chocolate cake.
Thank you for that too.
My mother told me
two days ago I was fat. So…
Oh, boy.
- This is nice, huh?
- It is nice.
How's he doing?
You know what?
He's got good days. He's got bad days.
You went through it.
You know what that's about.
- It's not a good time in your life.
- No, it's not.
- Yeah.
- It is what it is.
I know I don't see Pam a lot.
How's the pregnancy?
You know better than I.
Uh… Really… hormonal.
There's days where
I gotta leave the house.
What is wrong with you?
You don't understand women.
- I'm very patient.
- I know how you are.
She gets on a roll and then you walk out
and go in the gym
or you're going skydiving
or you're going to the polo field. Escape.
You can't do that
when someone is pregnant.
You just have to be there
and just shut up.
Just shut up and just be there.
- Okay.
- Anyway.
We gotta go. Let's go.
- Pour out your coffee.
- I already drank my coffee.
My mother-in-law…
My mother-in-law.
She's fucking nuts.
She's absolutely crazy.
You good?
She is the only one
that can really speak to me.
So she tells me to go fuck myself.
She tells me
to stop being a fucking idiot. Um…
She's a pain in my ass sometimes,
but I do appreciate it.
I appreciate everything that woman does.
- Louis, Louis, Louis.
- Hi, Yaya.
Very cool.
My dad used to have
his pilot's license.
He loves planes, helicopters.
I think it was a lovely gesture
to go and pick up my parents
and bring them to the game.
Any moment I get with my dad is special.
Smile.
All righty.
We lost to Valiente.
We're playing against Tamera.
If we lose now, the whole season is over.
Just like that.
This is the bet
that I placed this morning.
What?
- I put my house on this game. Yes.
- You put your house on this game?
This is the most important game
of the season.
The most important tournament for us.
We go into this game prepared,
ready to go.
It's do-or-die.
We're a couple rounds into
the U.S. Open Championship Tournament,
our grand finale,
and the final leg of the gauntlet here.
And La Fe
is coming off of a loss
against the Valiente 12-7 on Tuesday.
Tamera, they lost their
top scorer, Diego Cavanagh, to an injury.
So a different team
than we've seen normally.
Tamera,
their nine-goal player got hurt.
So they changed the team around.
We're gonna be
better off playing against this team
because the team is not as strong.
The umpires
have called the teams
looking to get this match underway.
Okay.
Chukker one off and working.
Looks like it's gonna be
one here by Zavaleta.
Now, Matias takes off running
towards the goal right here.
All they can do is hope he misses.
He's in the red zone.
Mati is gonna draw first blood on the day.
A shot back down the field from Matias.
Back up there looking for Mackey.
And look at this.
Two in a row. Bam, bam.
Score two goals.
Goes straight to the ball, takes it away.
Going to the goal.
Oh my God. Come on, would ya!
No one is there.
Beautiful goal. 3-0.
Tamera is cooking.
Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
Look at this. It's gonna be a goal
right here. Elizalde's not gonna miss.
He's on a breakaway.
And we've got a 3-2 score on the board.
Great way to finish a chukker for La Fe.
They didn't start well,
but they're back in the game.
They're back in the game. All right.
- You've got snacks in your purse.
What do you want me to do?
Not steal snacks from the buffet.
- Oh, shut up.
- She has lost her mind.
Bilbao takes a shot
from about 80 yards out.
It's going, going, going.
Devaleix is there. Devaleix shoots.
But I heard a whistle.
No goal scored there.
Most common foul,
a defender cannot come across
that right-of-way or the line of the ball
and make a play on the ball.
- Wait, so it doesn't count?
- No.
Here it comes.
Up to Louis.
- Louis needs to come up.
- Come on.
Come on!
Come on, boy!
- Come on, Louis!
- Louis!
Louis Devaleix! Oh.
He didn't do it?
I think I'm gonna give Louis
a backhand for missing that one.
It's very difficult.
- He's going 30 miles an hour.
- So what?
That will end
the first half, tied at six goals apiece.
We're gonna invite you out there
to walk back a few divots.
Going into to this game, I'm feeling
like we're gonna fucking… kill them.
We completely underestimated
what Tamera ended up bringing.
Fuck.
The field's clear.
It's ready for you all fine folks
to get out there
and stomp those divots back.
Don't forget to grab
a glass of bubbly on your way out there.
A halftime divot stomp,
a very old tradition.
Middle of the game,
the crowd comes out,
everybody goes onto the field,
and you stomp the divots
to ensure that the field is nice and flat
for the second half.
Stomp, stomp, stomp.
You get to see the outfits,
the colors, all of the people,
the kids running around.
Then all the people come back in,
and the game resumes.
- How about, "We're off to see the wizard"?
- No.
♪ We're off to see the wizard
The wonderful wiz--♪
I'm pregnant. Stop jerking me around.
You watch every one
of Louis' games?
Yeah. Well, he can do better.
- He could do better?
- Yeah.
What is he doing wrong?
Why don't you explain
what you think we should go tell Louis?
He should hit the ball straighter
is what I think.
Do you know polo?
I don't care. It's a stick,
and you hit a ball.
No fouls. Let's go! Come on.
The players coming back out.
- Here we go.
This is an important chukker
for both teams.
It's not the chukker
when you want to do mistakes.
Yeah.
So this is a big moment right now
for La Fe.
If they can get something
on this drive right now.
Look at this. Look at this.
If they score here,
this could be a huge play.
Matias Torres right now goes to the ball.
Goes to the goal. Picks it up nicely.
Zavaleta.
Uh-oh…
Louis, that might be a big mistake here.
Penalty two.
Oh, my Lord.
Penalty two is
your second most severe penalty.
Thirty-yard undefended shot on goal.
Make it or miss it.
The attacking team is gonna get one swing.
Mackey.
Sends it on through.
Picks up the point
and gives his team a two-goal lead.
Come on, man. Just sock it to them.
Look at this.
Here, Elizalde.
Takes a shot at the goal. It's off.
Oh, he got it! We got a ball game now.
It's gonna be
a really good end of the game.
That was a huge goal.
Elizalde jumps back.
One goal ball game,
one minute left.
We need to make the next goal.
It sure is close.
Here it comes.
Now Bilbao's got possession,
gives it off to Diaz Alberdi.
He's hooked on the play.
- And the whistle.
- What just happened?
Diaz, an unscheduled dismount.
I think they got that pony
collected over there
and our expert medical staff
on the scene immediately here.
One-goal ball game.
Well, this is right down
to the wire.
So Diaz Alberdi back on his feet.
Foul against Tamera.
Getting a yellow card.
The yellow card.
The goal goes in favor of La Fe.
Automatic goal for La Fe.
We're back to a tied ball game.
The bell,
and that will end regulation time.
We're gonna have overtime!
The first team to score will win.
All right, Mom, here we go.
Our energy is coming back.
Ball's back into play.
Lucas Alberdi. Oh, he drops it there.
Elizalde feeds it right back up to him.
He's gonna jump on it right here
and takes a shot at goal.
That is…
…over the backline wide.
Oh, my Lord.
La Fe narrowly
missing the goal.
Well done.
Palma comes in there, broke up the play.
Robi back on it. They're inside the 60.
Lucas Alberdi shoots at the goal.
It's gonna be wide.
Come on. Oh, Lordy me.
Torres Zavaleta breaks the goal.
Torres-Avoleta. Torres-Avoleta.
- Shit.
- Tamera!
Tamera, the victors. What a match.
What a game. Let's hear it for both teams,
ladies and gentlemen.
It all happened so fast.
We're like, "What the fuck is going on?"
I'm glad we're not going home with you.
I'll go home with you guys.
We went into this game
way too confident. It fucked us.
We're going back to the Keys
because I know how Louis feels.
We were gonna spend the night,
and I'm going… "Not a good idea."
Oh my God, you have churros in your purse.
Hasta la vista, baby.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
After that game with Tamera,
my mother said my dad would be proud.
My father was an amazing man, but tough.
Losing was never an option,
but in the end, he was always there
to make me feel better.
I wish he was still here.
With the 12-11 win
by Tamera over La Fe,
La Fe is now out of contention
for this year's U.S. Open.
Sorry, Mama.
He puts a lot of thought
and effort,
and so this isn't gonna go away for him.
This loss will be in the back of his head
for the next six months.
What went wrong, why it went wrong,
what they can do better,
that doesn't go away.
That stays with you, stays with him.
I'm gonna count.
Touch the post and come back.
On your mark, get set, go! One…
And it's used as fuel and motivation
to help build and learn from.
Okay, high five.
Had my worst game.
Every play, you know,
from the fucking beginning.
I feel like I'm complete… fucking garbage.
Well, because you feel like
you let your whole team down,
and it's not just the three guys,
you're letting your wife down.
- Even though she's there to pick you up.
- I'm sorry, honey.
I'm tired of losing.
Winning would have shown everyone
it wasn't a waste of their time.
- I'm going to the house. Meet you there.
- Yeah.
I'll get treats for the horses,
say good night, then go.
Okay.
- Love you. Bye, sweetheart.
- I'll see you at home.
Good night, guys.
I'm so mad.
Fuck.
He's being really, really hard on himself.
I just can't fucking win.
But it's more
than just winning and losing.
I think there's time for appreciating
the other parts of the sport, like this.
I wish he could get joy
out of these moments.
I'm fucking tired, man.