This is it.
The U.S. Open is underway.
And we have Dutta Corp
taking on Park Place.
We decided Timmy's gonna play number one.
Ball's put back into play.
Gonna be picked up here by Timmy.
Here we go. There we go. Come on!
Going to the goal,
he's got nothing between him and the goal.
Can he get it done?
Dutta in the red zone.
Timmy Dutta.
Oh no, it got away from him!
Oh man, Dutta Corp
really could have used that goal.
Hit the ball!
Let's hope their luck changes
after that one.
- Come on, guys.
- Jesus.
Timmy!
Change!
Yeah, I can hear him.
Why do you stay away from him?
Because I don't like
to hear him criticize Timmy.
Stop fucking around.
Hit the ball, Timmy. Hit the fucking ball.
I should be used to it by now.
It's been an exciting game so far,
and Dutta Corp has held their own
against Park Place.
And now, starting the third chukker,
the score is two to two.
Now, ball's put back into play.
Now, gonna be picked up again here
by Juan Britos.
Britos, going to the goal.
Once these guys get hot,
they get lava hot.
Unbelievable!
Come on guys, enough!
Unbelievable.
What a goal. Important timing too.
Dutta Corp really needs to score here.
If you give Park Place too big of a lead,
you're never gonna catch them.
Here comes Timmy Dutta.
Busting out of there, on a rocket ship.
He is cooking down the field.
Can he make it happen?
From left to right.
Dutta cuts the ball back at the goal…
Just wide over the back line.
You gotta make that count.
Really a tough break there for Dutta.
Unfortunately, it doesn't look like
they're gonna be able to best Park Place
here in this first game of the U.S. Open.
Tough loss.
Definitely for us and, you know…
My first game with this switch
with me in number one position.
I really needed the… the few chukkers
to get back in rhythm.
Good job, baby girl. You tried.
My dad doesn't get after me
from, like, a son perspective.
He gets after me
from, like, a player perspective.
He demands nothing but the best.
"Here's your chance.
Now get the job done."
I'm always grateful
for the opportunities that he gives me.
What I see,
what I feel, is what he hears.
Sometimes Susie feels that's too direct,
but so be it.
You know, he has big goals,
and we have big expectations together.
So every day, we have to move forward.
Otherwise, you're not going to get there.
We play Clearwater on Sunday.
Probably the most important game
for us the entire season.
We already lost against Park Place.
Have to win this game no matter what.
To play
the United States Open Championships,
it's an honor, and it's a dream.
Right now, we are trying to win our first.
What's going on?
His chica's coming into town?
News to me.
Think they're coming?
Timmy is extremely charming,
and his looks are what they are.
He doesn't have to worry about girls.
Score the goals!
Unfortunately, these girls take
a lot of time out of you.
They don't understand that you've got
to focus, and it's a distraction.
- I hope he's focused on Sunday.
- Yeah, he will.
Good.
Okay, here we go.
Let's go with that arm.
María now!
- It's forward back, forward back.
- Forward, back.
And come here and pass here.
I'm trying like fucking hell.
They make me work hard.
Very hard.
Who works harder?
- Me.
No. No.
Me. 49.
- Professor, tell them the truth.
- No.
- Who's the best of all three?
- Me.
I do the same as her.
- Shut up!
- In the gym and then I play.
- No!
- When she's drinking coffee.
Sí, and then who goes
to the supermarket and feeds you?
Me. So I won.
I'm telling you.
We love to train together.
So usually we all do it at the same time.
I mean, fucking hell.
The U.S. Open is one
of the most important
tournaments in the world.
Anybody that is in this sport
wants to win the U.S. Open.
My family, I have two candidates for that.
Poroto and Adolfo.
They're not playing on the same team,
which is hard for the family
because they may have to play
against each other.
I'm dying.
- Coach…
- What happened?
You guys, look.
Look at the difference, yeah?
Poroto really wants this tournament, um,
but the thing is Adolfo wants it too.
You know, my husband,
even though he's doing amazing,
he's in the retirement process.
I'm trying to be as competitive
as I can in the next year or so.
So I think one more,
it would be great for him.
Adolfo is very competitive.
Winning is in his DNA.
And he's the best of the best.
Good.
Yeah, let's go.
People say that you're the greatest
of all time. Do you agree with that?
I feel like there is always,
always somebody better than me.
Always. But I love competing.
Always, every day, I try to be better.
For me, to win, yes, beautiful day.
But the following day, you start
working to win the next tournament.
My father was a surfer.
Nothing to do with polo.
My mother was, uh,
just a weekend polo fan.
My first job as a professional polo player
was when I was 14.
I was getting paid by my father
with a motorbike, so it was kind of fun.
My friends were going out on Saturdays,
having life like a normal kid does.
Then I was competing,
going around the world.
I was alone, too young.
It was tough in one moment.
I was very lucky
to meet, uh, María, my wife,
when I was… 19 years old.
I met my husband
on the cover of a magazine.
He was, like,
they chose him as the best polo player
and me as the best model.
I didn't know, he was so good-looking,
so I just fell in love.
I didn't care what he was doing, so.
So now, polo is everything
in our family and even for my children.
In 2005,
it was a really big moment for me.
My husband was playing
one of the final games
of the Open in Argentina.
María was with her belly like that.
The doctor called him.
I was in the middle of the game.
I was on the horse like that.
María is about to give birth.
Adolfo's partners were asking him,
"Please don't leave. If you leave,
maybe we're gonna lose."
I left right away with the boots
and the whites and everything.
That year, Poroto came to life.
When Poroto was 12 years old,
I was already… 42.
I was nearly to retire.
My back was really hurting me.
But I would see Poroto grow
as a polo player really fast.
So I said,
"I need to play with him one day.
Why not?"
It was the Gold Cup, we won.
A U.S. Open. We did it, we won.
Then we said,
"We gotta play the Argentine Open."
Adolfo.
Adolfo Cambiaso again.
And we did it. And we won.
I couldn't believe
what we achieved together.
We played together,
we won everything together.
Now we're playing against each other.
La Dolfina.
I think it's the best team right now.
These guys are good. They're playing well.
I'm playing La Dolfina.
My dad is playing Valiente.
How does it feel
to play against your son?
Uh, it's not comfortable.
But it's all right.
You gotta get used to it,
but it's not easy.
I'm really close with my dad.
We have a really good relationship.
For me, it was a great experience
to… to share a field with my dad.
And he's the best teacher.
But I think that I can do more.
Poroto is going through a stage
where he's becoming a man.
It's time for Poroto
to start building his career
besides Adolfo.
It's time for him to start winning
by himself and against his father.
I think it's healthy.
I think it's about time.
The best situation
in the U.S. Open,
I want Valiente in the final
against our team, La Dolfina.
The only thing that I want
is to win against him.
I'm very proud of my son.
But I try to beat him.
Watch when they play each other.
The father's not giving in.
The son's not giving in.
They're going all out to make the plays.
It's kind of drama,
to be honest, for all of us.
But the good thing is
if they get there to that final game,
a Cambiaso will win.
Does everyone want
to beat the Cambiasos as bad as you do?
As bad as I do? I don't think so.
The Cambiasos have a target
on their back because they always win.
I mean, how can you not want to beat them?
At one point, it gets fucking old.
There's very, very few ten-goalers
like Adolfo Cambiaso and Poroto out there.
There's a handicap system in polo.
So the handicap system
in the U.S. Open is
each player has a handicap from
between minus one when you're a beginner
and then the top-top level is ten.
For the U.S. Open,
all four players' handicaps
must add up to 22.
Most professional players are rated
somewhere between three and eight goals.
There is less than eight ten-goal players
right now in the entire world.
We have some amazing
ten-goal players in the U.S. Open.
Most notably is,
of course, Adolfo Cambiaso
and his son, Poroto Cambiaso.
My handicap,
I mean, right now is, is one.
The goal is to get my handicap
to go up as much as possible.
We haven't missed,
uh… a workout this whole season.
No.
It's such a hard sport to tackle,
especially at, you know,
I was 40 when I first picked it up.
I have to work extra hard
to do what's best for the team.
And it's, you know, it's my team,
so I don't want to let the boys down.
What the fuck am I doing here?
Foul, it's how it is.
Foul.
Robi and I started La Fe together
three years ago.
What separates La Fe
from every other team?
I think that all of us,
we really care about one another.
The La Fe team, they're referred
to as the fraternity house.
They walk in as a pack.
They're together
off and on the field.
They party together.
They work out together.
It's like a family.
He and Robi built the team
and the organization that way.
You know? To have fun.
Louis is more than a leader.
He has a really good heart.
He don't like to follow what everybody do.
He wanna do something new.
La Fe are still kind of
the new kids on the block.
Because they are newer,
they are kind of an underdog team.
Every single player could be
making more money at another organization.
The fact that they want to be part
of La Fe makes me want to be able
to win with those three motherfuckers
that much more.
With what he does in the gym
and his approach to every day,
obviously that's why
he's able to do what he's doing.
It's a different,
different kind of mentality, you know.
Leading up to the U.S. Open,
I just think that I owe it
to the three professional players,
um, to work extra hard.
Every day I'm not on a horse,
I feel like I'm… I'm fucking things up.
And now today, instead of practicing,
I've gotta go to a baby shower.
We've got our baby shower today,
and I'm very excited.
It's my first baby and I feel like
it's a wonderful way to celebrate
bringing a new life into this world.
And more importantly, typically
my mom and my dad are in Chicago,
as are my siblings.
My polo girlfriends,
they are scattered across the globe.
So having everyone here to kind of share
that moment with them is really special.
Look who's here.
Hi. Oh my gosh, how are you?
Sorry, we're getting everything together.
My sister has planned everything.
She's done a beautiful job.
- That's in there.
- Got it.
Just bring it on in.
Thank you, I appreciate it.
In 2020, Kelley was a participant
in a show called The Bachelor.
Louis and I, we love the name Alina,
and her middle name is Kelley
after my amazing sister.
Where do we want to set this up?
Did we decide? In the front?
I'm trying to make sure
my sister is not stressed.
It's about her today.
So I just want to make sure
that we keep her calm.
Hi, guys. How are you?
The AC just went out. Holy hot.
The manager just came, said the AC is out.
They wanna move all of this
across the way to the pavilion.
- Okay.
- There's gonna be 80 people in here.
There's no way we can have
100 degrees plus 80 people.
Um, let me go get my phone.
We just got wind that the AC was out.
So now we're in this confused state.
It starts in 15 minutes
and we have zero AC.
Hey, how are you? The AC is out.
Baby. This is Louis Devaleix.
- I'll let you deal with that.
- I got a pregnant wife.
You guys gotta move this stuff
to the restaurant.
My wife is sweating her balls off.
There's only ten people in here.
We're not doing it in here.
It's not fair. It's not cool.
Just have everybody here so they can
move all the shit down there ASAP.
Wait.
Do you understand
how long this is going to take?
An hour or two hours out.
I'm not gonna be like that for two hours.
Want me here two hours, I'm not doing it.
I get it. I'm pregnant. I'm hot. But…
The AC was broken.
Shit wasn't ready on time.
My ultimate focus right now
is… is to win the U.S. Open.
We weren't practicing
when everybody else was practicing.
I'm so fucking mad.
Instead of that, I'm at a baby shower.
And I just really
did not want to be there.
It was definitely too late
to change the venue location.
Guests were already arriving.
Any luck with the AC units?
I believe they're coming right now.
Sorry about that.
It's not your fault.
Here you go.
Hi, everybody.
Welcome to Pamela's bri-- baby shower.
I hope we all have a good time here
because it's very, very hot.
Okay, so the AC,
we just got portable ones.
Everyone is steaming,
but hopefully it's okay.
Yeah, we'll see. We'll see. Okay.
My mom.
She's nuts in the best way,
but she's nuts.
She says things with such sincerity
that even if they're rude,
you know it comes
from a good place in her heart.
It's unfortunate that it's kind of
a shitshow because of the heat.
I know, because look at you guys.
You're all sweating too, like pigs.
No offense intended.
It's so fucking hot. It's so hot.
Am I allowed to start drinking?
- How are you? Good.
Thank you. Appreciate it. How are you?
I thought men weren't allowed
at these things.
Her mother made me come. Yeah, so.
My mom said, "You're gonna be there."
He said, "Men don't go to baby showers."
And she said, "Yes, they do."
Hi, Yaya. How are you doing?
You're wearing a T-shirt
to the baby shower?
Yes, ma'am.
Why would you not wear a collared shirt?
Gym shoes and those pants.
- You look like he's baling hay in a barn.
- White shirt…
Do you think
you're going to a rib barbecue?
Mom!
Nobody can push
that man around like my mom can.
In my family,
the tradition is the dads stop by.
Yeah, it was very important
for Louis to be there.
Do you know, Yaya,
men normally don't come to these events.
- Yes, they do.
- They do not.
I'm looking forward
to, uh, everybody sitting down
so that your daughter can give her speech,
so I can get the fuck out of here.
You better say something too.
- I'm not saying anything.
- Why not? You're the dad, aren't you?
I wanna thank you girls
for putting this event together.
Baby, you are, uh, fantastic.
Our daughter is so very lucky
to have you as her mother.
You hold this family together
and I love you very much,
and I thank you for all you do.
Thank you very much.
Who will take
more photographs of the baby?
Who will be the more strict parent?
Who will want more children sooner?
Thank you, guys all for coming
to celebrate my little perfect niece,
baby Alina Kelley.
Louis, you are free. You can go.
Love you.
The fucking baby shower.
There's nothing more important
than… than staying laser focused
to try and win this tournament
because the competition is just fierce.
I can't eat this.
I don't eat dairy anymore.
Why not?
- Nothing will happen.
I don't eat mozzarella.
Give it to me.
I'm Keko Magrini.
I'm 18 years old,
and this year I'm playing for Coca-Cola.
I'm the kid. I'm the youngest on the team.
I try to learn every day.
They're older than me, and I can learn
from all of them something.
Yeah, sometimes I get a little yelled at.
I yelled at you to go left.
So you go ahead, grab him faster.
This year
I started feeling pressure.
Maybe it's just me, myself,
putting too much pressure on me.
It really… It's not easy.
Stolen away by Matias Magrini.
My dad, Matias Magrini,
was a ten-goal player.
Matias Magrini shoots,
Magrini scores!
My father never
pushed me into anything.
I do it because I like the sport.
It's a different adrenaline.
I mean, you don't feel it
with many other things.
It's… it's amazing.
Tough draw
for the U.S. Open this year, no?
Yes, rough.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
When we drew,
we draw Valiente,
which has Adolfo Cambiaso.
La Dolfina, which was Poroto.
Pilot, which was Facundo Pieres.
Then we draw Clearwater,
which was a tough team.
Playing in the U.S. Open, you're always
competing against the best in the world.
You still can
with a bit of luck.
- Yes, but…
- No?
We'll see.
♪ Hopped on a saddle
Racing like a comet ♪
♪ Jumping every hurdle
Ain't nothing to stop it… ♪
My girlfriend, Marissa,
she rides on the show jumping.
I spend some time with her there
whenever she shows or she rides.
We have the same season at the same time.
We try to figure out
how to spend time together.
You try, but you're also
nervous about the games.
♪ Gravity defined
What we'll make in the balance… ♪
Thank God.
I go really soon, and you weren't here,
and I was getting nervous.
It's their fault.
- Are you going to set jumps?
- No.
You don't want to set them with Paula?
Your loss.
It's not always the easiest
to date someone who eats,
sleeps, and breathes polo.
But Keko does a good job
at making time for me.
With his schedule and his lifestyle,
it's not easy, and I'm difficult.
I, like, want attention.
Can I tell you the course?
- What?
- Can I tell you the course?
- Okay. Yeah, one to two is a ten.
- Like, you really don't have to.
- Can you pay attention? No, get off.
- I am.
I am paying attention.
Keko and I, we've been dating for a year.
In the months
we got to know each other,
we enjoyed spending time
with each other. It was really fun.
And yeah, it just ended up working out.
Okay, I need to get ready.
I'm going to go get on soon.
- Okay, go get them.
- Can you come with me to get ready?
Yeah,
because I'm getting really anxious.
Please?
Up now is number 674, Marissa Rice.
She looks good going into her first jump.
Her horse unexpectedly stopped
going into that number ten jump.
Her horse stopped there.
I don't know what happened.
That's not going in, right?
Hold this for a sec. What a day.
- So what happened? Why?
- He spooked.
The horse never spooked.
I don't know. He saw a ghost.
- Should we go get a smoothie?
- Yeah, we can go get a smoothie.
Keko is very much an internalizer.
He keeps the emotions in.
We've spent a lot of time together,
so I definitely can feel the vibe out
and the moods out.
He has a huge organization
backing him in this sport.
A lot goes into him
being out there on those horses,
and I think sometimes
he might feel like he lets people down
when there's that many people
behind him supporting him.
It's been hard because Negro,
who is a really good polo player,
got injured.
And Keko loves playing with Negro.
They have a great relationship
on and off the field.
How bad did he break it?
The whole thing or just one part?
- He broke it in two spots.
- Two spots?
- So he's out for the U.S. Open?
- He's out for the whole season.
I played with him last year.
Before it was the first time
I ever played with him, and I love him.
We became really good friends.
It's… the worst thing
that could've happened to us right now.
It's hard to replace Negro.
We just have to have good energy as a team
and yeah, maybe we have a shot at it.
Hopefully.
- Are you tired?
- I want to get the fuck outta here.
What a day, no?
Thank you for coming, though.
No problem.
We always have a dinner
with the families before games.
We are a close-knit team
and it shows on the field.
After the loss to Park Place,
it's very important for us
to win against Clearwater.
- Hi, sweetheart.
Good to see you.
- You ready for tomorrow?
Oh, yeah.
We can beat any team
on any given day if it's our day.
We've got to focus,
and we have to be better.
I feel pressure from my father.
He wants to win so bad, and I get it.
But I think it's… it's healthy
to have somewhat of a… a personal life
outside of the sport and being an athlete.
- Hi. Hi, Charlie.
- Hi.
I met a really nice girl, Eva.
Hi.
Gorgeous,
like an incredible personality.
- I'm Susie.
Hi, Karina. Nice to meet you.
Oh, this is your mom?
- This is my mom.
I'm good.
- Nice to see you.
- Mucho gusto.
We went on one date,
and she went off to Paris.
- You're gorgeous!
- You look amazing!
She flew back
to spend a long weekend,
and it was her birthday as well.
- Hi.
- How are you?
So I decided to invite her to
the team dinner with her and her family.
Sometimes you gotta do what you gotta do.
Oh my God, how many dogs do you have?
Too many, but bear with us and come on in.
I would really love Timmy
to be with somebody that is kind
and supportive.
I don't know if you have it.
It's a French photographer.
Hoping you like it.
That's so sweet.
Oh, it's beautiful.
Oh, this is beautiful.
Timmy's my baby.
I have my opinions about,
you know, who he's dating.
I think she liked the book.
We want the right person.
- Tim, what do you think about Eva?
- She's amazing, but, you know.
Do you think Timmy
really likes this girl?
I don't know.
We know nothing. We see nothing.
Okay, everybody, it's time to eat.
Come on, let's go, guys.
The pasta's getting cold.
Right now,
he needs to concentrate on himself
and being the best polo player
that he can possibly be.
- You're good? You want any salad?
- No, I'm okay.
At least through the Open, please.
Eva, welcome. Happy birthday.
Thank you.
And to celebrate new friendships.
To have romance during
the U.S. Open is definitely difficult.
It's one of those things
you don't have much time for.
But at the end of the day,
I want the stars and the moon.
I'm not happy with just the moon.
I want the stars too.
So for me to achieve that,
I dream about the perfect connection,
the perfect balance.
So that way,
I can live up to my potential.
Boys, tomorrow is a big day for us.
Be safe,
play hard,
and bring it home.
To all the best.
♪ Look at me go, look at me go ♪
♪ Heavy on the go
We don't ever calm down… ♪
I'd like to welcome you.
Happy to have you all
on a beautiful Sunday afternoon.
Two great teams here,
and it should be pretty even.
- You ready, boys?
Sunday polo is the chance for us
to play on an incredible stadium
and a great atmosphere.
It's like playing
center court in Wimbledon.
It's the best venue in America
and top three in the world.
Field one,
U.S. Polo ASSN field number one,
is the cathedral of North American polo.
That's the field that every polo player,
especially American, wants to play on.
The stadium gives you
a little bit of sparkle.
You get the energy from the crowd.
Everybody comes and watches.
They put their Sunday hat on
and a cute outfit.
Fashion is almost more important
than the actual game.
I don't know anything about it.
I just came for the food and the outfit.
I've been coming for years.
We appreciate the skills
that these riders have.
This is not an easy sport.
To me, it's like Christmas every Sunday.
It's exciting, and it's dangerous.
I'm a little nervous
just because now that I have someone
to personally root for,
it's more, you know, anxious,
but I… I have full trust
that he's going to play great.
Clearwater, they're a good team.
They play very well.
In terms of horses, Dutta Corp
and Clearwater are evenly matched,
so it's gonna come down to
who has the better game plan.
The Dutta Corp is
coming into this game after a loss.
Timmy Dutta,
up in the number one position,
he hasn't played in that position
in a long time
and he's struggling a bit
to find his footing.
Coming out of Park Place,
a few mistakes that we had,
we'll fix,
and it'll make a big difference.
Play with your brain, huh?
Execute.
Clearwater is the one game
we have to win no matter what,
to give us a shot to continue on.
Hopefully, we can go get it done.
Look to the center field
to get the match started.
- The nerves are really kicking in.
- Here we go.
Clearwater in the white.
Dutta in the blue.
Let's go, Dutta Corp!
The ball is thrown in…
and we are off to the races.
First one there,
Garcia Del Rio pumps one downfield.
But on the defense,
Jared Zenni losing the play momentarily.
Come on. Come on.
Timmy Dutta.
Go, Timmy, go.
Fires one to goal…
And the first blood goes to Dutta Corp.
Gus, they moved Timmy to number one.
- And we saw that strategy working.
- Love it.
They're doing good.
The team is working.
Let's see if the Dutta Corp
can keep this momentum going here
early in the game.
I was finding a lot of space
in the front to be able to pull the team.
He's done it again.
Dutta, Dutta day!
The horses were on point,
and the balls were reaching Timmy,
and he created havoc.
Over to Timmy Dutta.
Timmy Dutta reaching for it
with a shot on goal,
and he finds the mark.
- More intense, Timmy.
- Relax.
If I go more intense,
somebody's gonna get hurt.
He just annihilated them.
It's now 13-8.
13… 13-4.
I guess Clearwater wishes it was 13-8.
Okay, 13-4.
Come on, guys.
We're back on the center line.
The ball is in play.
Out of the pack.
It's… taken here by Timmy Dutta.
Timmy, has he hit it too far?
Can he get there in time?
He does!
No, he's had a hot mallet.
He's played very well.
And he's really, really improved
in the last season or two. Timmy Dutta.
All the hard work paid off that day.
But the victory will go
to Dutta Corp today.
Oh my God. Just…
- And our MVP today is…
- MVP!
Timmy Dutta.
That game
was super important for us.
Clearwater is the one team
that we had to beat.
So that we're still in the fight.
Timmy, fantastic game today.
You're on fire.
Run us through the game
from your perspective.
This is our first big win
of the season, and for us,
Clearwater is a very talented team.
All the players are amazing
and well-mounted
so I'm proud of the horses
and everybody else's teammates
did a great job.
Awesome. Thank you so much, Timmy.
Congratulations again.
- Good luck through the tournament.
- Thank you very much.
Appreciate it. Happy Easter, y'all.
When we win,
we always get a little happy about it.
We have some drinks, dance a little bit.
Enjoy the polo club.
What's the next step?
Valiente.
Valiente. Get 'em!
We'll get 'em.
What I want for Timmy is to become
the best polo player he possibly can
and win some great cups.
I think that he has a bright future.
We just have to keep him rolling
in the right way.
It's so much fun.
I couldn't have asked
for more welcoming parents.
It's special that we get to all root
someone that we care about.
And… we'll see… we'll see what happens.
- Eva picked a good weekend.
- She did, she did.
Maybe she was the reason we won.
You never know.
It could be that special touch
that just sent us to a different level.
I told her to come for the next game,
but she couldn't.
One of the biggest games
of the season.
We're playing against Cambiaso.
And if you can beat them,
it sets the tone for the rest.
Most players just like to take it easy,
warm up, and then relax.
And I like to go
and play against another player.
I like to be able to feel the adrenaline
and prepare, you know,
for the contact sport.
And then 20 minutes before the game,
I show up on the field.
I'm feeling nervous.
- Vamos!
- But good nervous.
Welcome to the National Polo Center
here in Wellington, Florida.
We're about to get the game underway,
where we're gonna see
La Fe take on Valiente.
As always, Valiente is one of
the favorites here to win the U.S. Open.
These guys are…
It's a tough team.
For sure.
I don't think…
I don't think we've ever
actually got a chance to beat them.
When you think of polo,
you think of Cambiaso.
I think he's played
the U.S. Open almost 20 times.
He's also playing
on some spectacular horses, dude.
Like, they're very well mounted.
Adolfo Cambiaso
and Valiente understand
that in polo the horses
are so, so very important.
Each one of those horses
they bring to the field… Top, top horses.
Every single chukker.
Adolfo Cambiaso,
they tell me they own 3,000 horses.
Yet, somebody comes along
with a good horse, he buys another one
because he's looking
for those horses that really perform.
Bob Jornayvaz is, um,
the sponsor of the Valiente polo team.
He and Adolfo have been playing together
for many years now.
When you've got that kind of money
for the tournament,
it makes a difference.
La Fe, they have
a tough job to win this game.
Cambiaso, there are not
many people who beat him,
so maybe we will play
a little bit more together today.
How is Louis feeling today?
He's more nervous than us,
so he's just going to stick and ball now.
I was starting to feel good,
feel really confident.
We've over prepared for this,
so we're ready.
This is our game.
They beat us two years ago and last year.
We're gonna beat 'em.
Both teams are starting
to get ready, doing their warm-ups,
as people are pulling up,
getting ready to watch this game
here in Wellington, Florida.
I go thinking
I'm always going to lose.
I really believe that the other team
is much better than mine.
I go with that fear to every game.
In order
for La Fe to beat Valiente,
they're gonna have to play
at their very best level
because we know Valiente comes to win
every time they go to the field.
Where the fuck is Louis?
So I was at the barns,
and all of a sudden,
I realize I lost track of time.
I was like… fuck.
I mean, who the fuck does that?
Not very ideal
to leave at three o'clock.
We got the biggest game of the year.
We're supposed to be normally
at the field at this time already.
I'm not gonna fucking make it.
Fuck.