♪ You know the time is now… ♪
Despite having a bad U.S. Open,
I'm looking forward to any opportunity
to get better as a player.
I want to improve,
and Sentebale is great for that.
Sentebale, it's a charity
that was founded in 2006
by Harry and Prince Seeiso
in Lesotho, Africa.
Every year, we play one game
somewhere in the world.
This year it happens
in Wellington, Florida.
The outcome of today
is not about who wins it.
It's Sentebale that wins,
and that's what we're all here for.
This is cool.
- Very cool, right?
- Yeah.
In charity matches
like the Sentebale Polo Challenge,
the pressure of the U.S. Open
is off for just a moment.
Players get to come together
and have a bit of fun
and raise some money for a great cause
and entertain a big crowd.
But the polo itself is still top tier.
Most people go there.
It's a charity event.
Let's play easy polo and have a good time.
Are you gonna play, like,
friendly?
- Very friendly.
- Okay.
I'm a very friendly person.
Friendly, remember that.
I'm here to become
a better player,
and… you know, just want to fucking win.
- Huh?
- Dude, you're done.
Yeah, dude, we fucking suck.
It was so bad.
It was just such a bad season.
You're, like, supposed to progress
every year, you know, with the same team.
We just suck.
To be part of
a Sentebale event is awesome.
You have all
the best players in the world.
You know,
I was playing on a team with Nacho,
and then Prince Harry and Cambiaso
were playing together on another team.
- How's the Open?
- Poroto is a star now.
He is. He is.
- You created something special.
- Yeah.
He's doing amazing things.
For him,
he's starting the career.
- He's only 18?
- 18.
- How old were you when you became ten?
- Uh, similar.
- Similar, but-- Okay.
- He beat me.
We play together a lot.
You can play with your kid,
something that you love.
Yeah, but what's it like
playing against your kid?
It's difficult.
And worse when you lose.
- You're proud, but also angry.
- Yeah. Exactly.
- Is he here today or not?
- Yeah, he's here.
He wants to meet Poroto.
- Hi. How are you?
- Nice to meet you. I'm good.
Nice to see you.
Are you going to end up
in the final against your dad?
- Are you gonna dispatch him before that?
- The semifinals is by draw.
So we gotta be lucky
not to play against each other.
You could play each other
in the second?
Once you get to the fourth semifinalist,
you go by draw.
Everyone may be playing
for a good cause,
but we are still in
for some heart-pounding polo.
Ladies and gentlemen,
let's get ready to get this game underway.
Might decide
to run this one himself.
What a cracking goal here.
Sentebale Polo Challenge
is, uh, played in a round-robin format.
Six chukkers. So we all play two chukkers
against the other two teams.
Whoever wins more games
is considered the winner.
Louis Devaleix.
Louis takes a touch.
And that's all he's going to need.
Louis Devaleix, ladies and gentlemen.
Louis just scored. I missed it.
Do it again, baby. Do it again.
I missed his goal. Do it again, baby.
So first game, I scored a goal.
- It's good that they're passing.
- It was a good game.
Nacho Figueras.
Where's that ball going to land?
Wow, what a great shot,
ladies and gentlemen.
We won.
So it just only accelerated that fuel,
that desire to win the tournament.
How are you feeling?
- Good. Ready to play.
- Next pregnancy.
Well picked up there
by the Duke of Sussex.
Adolfo. Here we have another possible run.
Dana Barnes, and he puts that one through.
Ladies and gentlemen,
what an amazing goal.
Hey! How are you, man?
Hello.
- Nice to meet you. Very well.
- How are you?
- She's fluent in Spanish.
- Really?
I lived there
about 20 years ago. In Palermo Viejo.
- Oh. In Palermo Viejo?
- Las Cañitas too.
That's great.
That's where the polo fields were.
Yes, but I love the 25th of May…
Yeah? That's great. Cool.
- Do you speak Spanish? No?
- Yes.
He knows I don't.
Yes.
- Well, yes.
- A little, a little. All right.
I still had to play Cambiaso.
Grand Champions and Sentebale.
We were both winners,
which kind of led to a virtual final
between us Grand Champions and Sentebale.
We're gonna beat them.
And, uh, Louis.
Louis Devaleix doing a very good job
beating the ten-goaler.
Louis Devaleix all the way
on a straight run to goal.
Borwick puts his mallet down
on the near side.
You're playing against
the biggest figures in the sport.
They're driven and… and motivated
for their own personal pride.
We crash each other.
Prince Harry was not relaxing,
and he wanted to win at all costs,
and I was the same way.
Prince Harry
on the move, working it.
Oh, what a run!
Ladies and gentlemen,
what a run and what a goal by the Prince.
Give it up, if you will,
for the Duke of Sussex.
Adolfo could just hammer one.
We got beat, at the end
of the day, a great day for the charity,
which is what is important to all of us.
I still can't win.
Thanks, dude.
- Thanks for having us. I appreciate it.
- It was fun.
Well done indeed.
The Royal Salute Polo Challenge
in aid of Sentebale 2024.
Coming in second place,
the boys in the white shirts,
Louis Devaleix.
Watching Louis playing,
that's a huge part
of the sport that I enjoy.
But at the same time,
it makes me want so badly to be out there.
Since the pregnancy,
I haven't been on a horse.
So I definitely am eager
to get back on a horse, for sure.
Polo Challenge
in aid of Sentebale
And the winners, Sentebale Royal Salute.
Put your hands together
for the Duke of Sussex,
Adolfo Cambiaso,
Dana Barnes, and Mr. Malcolm Borwick.
Hi. Hi.
Hi.
- Fucking devil.
Hey.
- How much shit did you eat?
Plenty.
- How much shit did you eat today?
- Be nice to her.
You stay.
When you get pregnant,
there's a new part of you that you gain,
but a part of you also that you lose.
I've always wanted to be a mother.
My whole life I've wanted kids.
But you're never really prepared
for that transition
until you experience it yourself.
I have definitely lost a part of myself
in certain moments
and felt really down about that.
When I couldn't ride,
I wasn't traveling for work.
I wasn't really doing the things
that make me… me.
I've been wanting to do it
for some time now.
And this is my baby,
so she won't do anything.
It's a tough thing to come to grips with
because going that long
without being on a horse
was really difficult.
And… …you know, when
you're having a baby, you start thinking,
"Will I get back into this?
I don't know how I'm gonna feel."
Where I'm gonna be physically,
mentally, emotionally. You don't know.
Push up. One, two, three.
Great.
I got her. I got her. Don't worry.
Oh, my baby girl.
Oh, I love this horse so much.
You happy?
She's gonna start crying.
I just missed her.
- We won't go anywhere, okay?
- Okay.
She loves the horses
more than she loves the game.
- I wouldn't miss that for the world.
- I love you, Stellie.
You'll be back on her in no time.
Yeah. Okay.
Even just that second of sitting on her,
it just kind of reaffirmed for me
that this is what I love.
It will always be part of my life,
no matter what stage of life I'm in.
I'm just grateful to have horses
as such a consistent part of my life.
Come on, come with us.
Getting back on was really special for me.
Come on.
We're going this way.
She's like, nah.
♪ Let's get this party goin' ♪
♪ Everythings in motion ♪
♪ You feelin' windy
But we keep on goin'… ♪
What a U.S. Open season
it's been.
We're down now to our semifinalists.
Valiente, Pilot, and La Dolfina have been
favored to make it this far all along.
But Coca-Cola really surprised us all
by securing their spot
and winning a penalty shootout
against Park Place.
Hilario Ulloa.
He missed it. It just goes to show
that when it comes to the U.S. Open,
anything can happen.
First one is Coca-Cola.
Coca-Cola will take on La Dolfina.
Valiente.
And Valiente will take on Pilot.
♪ Okay, tell 'em,
Tell 'em, tell 'em, tell 'em ♪
♪ Keep up with this ♪
Maybe Mala
is the tenth?
Yes. Tórula played, didn't he?
Yes.
To me, Mala is the best, isn't he?
- Two for Toro…
- He rode it?
Toro was gonna ride it,
maybe I'll tell him.
Fucking Louis catching fish.
That one catch is for, uh…
For Keko Magrini right there
for not coming out on the boat with us.
We're missing him.
'Cause Coca-Cola
made it to the semifinals,
so he's too cool to come out here with us.
That's all right, Keko. No worries.
This one's for you, baby.
Tell them
to take us tomorrow.
Yeah.
For Keko Magrini
right there for not coming on the boat.
We're missing him.
The match before,
Keko made a joke about canceling
our anniversary dinner that night.
And I think I took it
a little too seriously.
But it was a really fun night,
a really great dinner, good time together.
So, they made it to the semis.
It's a big one. I'll go be there for him.
I want him to win, and I want him
to be happy with how he played.
Three, two…
Once you get
to the finals, you just try to enjoy them.
You never know when
you're gonna play it again.
We had La Dolfina, and we knew
we can beat if we had a little luck.
I think we have
a really good draw
for the family.
We don't have to play
against my dad in the semifinals.
Now the thing that I want is we both win.
We're getting ready
for our first semifinals here.
We've got Coca-Cola taking on La Dolfina.
Poroto takes the man.
Panelo takes the ball.
First blood goes
to La Dolfina.
Big swing on that one
and a shot out in front.
Keko Magrini for Polito Pieres.
What a pass by Keko Magrini.
Poroto Cambiaso,
some big hang time on that ball.
It's heading in the right direction.
- What a shot.
- Right on target.
Fantastic marksmanship there by the kid.
Cut shot coming. What a goal.
- Running for the back line.
Fantastic.
Cambiaso needs a big
right-hand turn. Panelo, there he gets it.
Keko cannot give up
after that play.
I bet you Polito's not happy right now.
We can't let that play happen.
I've been fighting like this.
I look back and you come, galloping alone.
I swear it's not on purpose, man.
No, no, no.
You saw how that went?
And you went to… No, remember!
Poroto, you were with him.
- That's your man, that's your man.
- Okay.
The thing that polo has
is that you can get
within five goals in four minutes.
Let's go.
Come on, come on.
Be sharper, man, be sharper.
The shot to goal.
Keko Magrini, a needed goal for Coca-Cola.
Hopefully getting
his confidence rolling as well.
Coca-Cola's back on.
Polito, lofted shot.
He gets it. How about that?
Fucking hell.
Bang, bang.
Coca-Cola brings 'em within one.
No.
They are screwing up. They are gonna lose.
- Shut up!
- They are doing everything wrong.
Compact, they are great. This chukker
was amazing how they played it.
Come, let's go. Last stretch. Go!
Let's go! Come on!
We need to score two goals now, okay?
Let's see if Coca-Cola can stay
in that vein right now.
They can't tie this one up.
Polito Pieres
giving that ball a big ride inside.
One more could do it.
Knocked out of there by Panelo.
A touch by Toro.
Here comes Poroto Cambiaso on the move,
trying to get this ball
out of their half of the field.
Poroto Cambiaso.
Can he keep the run together? Poroto.
Keko Magrini coming on strong from behind.
- Nice. Wow-wee.
- Good, Poro.
Good, Poro!
There you go.
There you go. That's one.
Yes, finished!
Now yes! Bye!
Poroto Cambiaso.
- Poroto Cambiaso.
- Poroto Cambiaso, cannot stop him.
Keko Magrini fires to goal.
Does he have it? He does.
Keko, what a shot.
This just goes to show
the enormous potential that Keko has.
Unfortunately, he hasn't had
a great day on defense,
and La Dolfina won't stop scoring.
We'll see La Dolfina take
the "W" in the first of two semifinals.
You were great.
We wanted to be in the final,
and that played against us
in some moments.
We were, me, personally,
anxious, wanting to be in the final,
without thinking that I had
a very important semifinal ahead,
and at times, I'd lose my focus,
but I think I also had good moments,
and that's why also, we won.
You've gone
into the U.S. Open before
with your father on your team,
and now you might play against him
in the U.S. Open finals.
Uh, what is this like
for you guys as a family?
Good.
It's difficult, always,
to play finals against Dad,
but I hope he wins today.
It would be very nice.
The game ending
like this was also a little sad.
The whole season, it's been hard.
Keko, when he doesn't win,
it doesn't always show how much
effort and work is being put into
what's actually happening out there.
When you get
a great opportunity like that
you wanna do it right and not…
just throw it away,
that's why
you probably put pressure on yourself,
'cause you don't know
when you're gonna play again there.
It's how hard it is.
Polo's a hard sport,
and everybody has to show up together
and click for there to be success.
There's a lot of things
that go into a successful team.
These owners go out into the world,
they want the best athletes
that are gonna perform at their best.
So, you fall from that.
You don't become
a valuable player anymore for a team.
The future in Coca-Cola is no more future.
I mean, I'm not playing next year.
Polo is what
I want to do my whole life.
It's, uh, my only plan I have.
I didn't feel that it was my best season.
I didn't get to play…
what I know I can, or how I want to.
I mean, after you lost,
you're like, you cannot do anything there.
When I lose important games
or games that are tough,
I won't sleep.
I want that one.
Season's done.
Was it a stressful one, no?
I don't think it was fun.
We have to spend a lot of time together.
But why?
For Keko and I,
I don't know what's going on.
We say we're always going to be together,
and we're going to date forever,
and then end up together. It's hard.
Tensions and pressures,
during times like that, are pretty high.
Sometimes it's better
just to be alone, during the day,
and think about myself.
I felt Marissa understood it in some ways,
and in some other stuff
it must have been hard for her.
But it's what it was.
I'm dead.
You have so much more
to be happy about.
- Like what?
- With me.
Your girlfriend who you don't kiss.
When I was 20,
I could play a lot of games.
But… today, uh,
I need to take care of my body for sure.
I try to do a little bit of this,
stretching.
If not, I can be really sore.
I couldn't start at the beginning
of the season like everybody else,
because I had a lower back injury.
And for me to come back from that,
to get to the semifinals, it's important.
Yes.
I know that I can still compete against
these young, great kids that are coming.
This is better now.
So, I really hope we can make it
to the final of this Open,
because competing against Poroto
makes me have this adrenaline again
of trying to get better
and compete and win.
But, first of all,
I have to beat his father, Adolfo.
He's an amazing polo player.
A lot of years
of playing against each other.
- Facundo Pieres!
- Facundo!
- Cambiaso! Goal!
- Adolfo Cambiaso!
Facundo Pieres and Adolfo
have been number one and number two
for the past 15 years.
Socially,
they high-five each other
and they're friends when
they're having asados, but on the field,
as soon as a ball is hit, or a whistle,
they're like, "Oh yeah, let's go!"
Since 2015,
so for the last decade,
Valiente has won the U.S. Open twice
and Pilot has won the U.S. Open twice.
Both these teams are very hard to beat.
To get to be in a semifinal
for us was really a big deal.
But when Bob was in the hospital,
you know, I was just thinking about him.
We pray for him
and I hope, uh, he wakes up soon.
Um, we're waiting for him.
Many of my dreams in my polo career,
they came true.
But if I win in the semifinals,
I will play in a final
on a stage of the U.S. Open
against my son.
I never even dreamed about it.
Semifinal number two.
Pilot in white jerseys,
Valiente in their blues.
Going head-to-head here
to see who will face La Dolfina.
Here comes Facundo,
and then Adolfo jumps back on it.
We're gonna see a lot of action
between those two today.
Oh, it's left behind. Gonna be picked up
by Heguy. Can he sneak it inside?
Can he make him pay? Antonio Heguy!
And Pilot on the board first.
Chukker number one. Pilot on top by one.
- It'll happen, calm down.
- Let's go.
- It's long
- Good.
Nice moves
on the back line there from Valiente.
And we're even here at one.
Adolfo Cambiaso leads
the horse race out in front here.
Valiente in the lead over Pilot.
- Well done.
Can he get it done?
Gonzalez! Right on through.
Adolfo Cambiaso.
Adolfo, not easy to do.
Peke Gonzalez out in front.
He wants the pass. He gets the pass.
Peke Gonzalez on final approach.
Peke Gonzalez!
Valiente. These guys looking
to secure their spot in the finals.
Either I cut through
or you throw long, at the neck.
- It was great.
- But the play was good.
Curtis.
- We have to change everything.
- Okay.
I mean, it feels like
we have no play right now.
Okay.
Pass to me and see
if I can score a goal later.
Plenty of time.
Pilot needs to get to work.
Adolfo brings
the ball into play.
Paco gonna get caught
here on a right-of-way.
It's gonna be a penalty going in favor
of Pilot. They needed it.
Plenty of time left to go here.
If they can score here…
Facundo on the line.
And he missed it.
- Oh my goodness.
- Wow. You won't see that often.
On any given day, Facundo Pieres,
he can beat anybody on the planet.
But a little unlucky there
against Valiente.
He never quits.
He continues to fight.
Facundo Pieres starts
to drive inside. Hits it out in front.
Looking for Antonio Heguy.
Heguy, 20 yards out.
A roller along the ground. It's in.
They won't stop. I love it.
Facundo Pieres grabs control. Hits away.
Antonio's on the move.
He's got him beat.
If he can keep it going.
Antonio Heguy down Main Street.
He goes one more through the air. It's in.
That could be just what Pilot needs
to get back into this polo game.
It's not over yet.
- Adolfo.
- No bouncer doubted.
- What a goal.
Every time Pilot gets going,
Adolfo seems to have an answer.
Adolfo not letting Pilot
gain any momentum.
Ball's in play.
That's gonna be the last chance.
Facundo Pieres,
the inside track on Adolfo Cambiaso.
Oh, no.
Facundo,
maybe one in a thousand times
you'll see him miss that opportunity.
Wow.
Congratulations to Valiente.
- They had full control of the entire game.
- I agree.
Into the finals the two go.
It'll be a father-son shootout.
And it's gonna be a great final
against these two sister organizations.
They must be thrilled again
to make it to the finals.
We… we tried. We tried.
That's all we can do.
It never feels good to get beat,
but, uh, the shots that we normally
would make in our sleep,
we weren't able to make them,
so that's really what happened there.
He had injuries. I mean,
there's nothing you can do about it.
I knew when he, uh, hurt his back
the way he hurt it.
I knew we were climbing the hill,
and we were doing very well,
and it just… today wasn't the day.
It's difficult to get to a game
when you're sore,
so I think without the injuries,
we would have had our chances
a lot better at the semifinals.
But at the same time,
we had a very good year, I think.
It's fun to be in that position
at this time of my career,
you know, 49, not young.
I'm going to try to enjoy it,
and I'm just happy
to be in the final against my son.
Daddy against his son in the final.
Father against son.
Who do I want to win?
Uh, very hard question.
Adolfo always wants to win.
I… I don't even want to play
Monopoly with him. It's in his DNA.
Poroto, he's becoming a man,
so imagine, for me,
it's like all I wanted for him.
Today is a happy day.
Sunday, I will let you know
if it's going to be this happy.
It's a fitting culmination
to this season
to see father-son
settle it.
- Fanta, Louis?
- Give me that Coke.
I don't know what to tell you.
If you don't get a bite here,
good thing you're a polo player,
not a fucking professional fisherman.
But those are tiny bites.
I can guarantee you
there's big fish here.
There you go, baby. What you got?
- No, I lost it.
- You lost the fish, well.
To be continued.
- You guys almost won yesterday.
- It was good.
And you, boludo, what happens now?
Like, you're done with Coca-Cola?
Yes.
Coca-Cola,
they're letting Keko go.
This year was a tough year for Keko
for a variety of different reasons.
Obviously, performance wasn't up to par,
it wasn't up to the level
that Coca-Cola is used to playing at.
But I've been watching Keko
for a couple of years now,
and the way this kid improves,
I know for a fact that
he's gonna come out better and stronger.
We're gonna call your dad.
Let's call your dad.
I'm with your son right now.
I'm trying to corrupt and convince him
into playing with us next year.
Fucking corrupted, yeah.
That can be fucking corruption, yeah.
Send me a picture
with a fish, dude, with a fucking fish.
We don't have a fish.
We don't catch shit.
We said,
"We want to play with you."
And Keko said,
"I really want to play with you too, now."
But the stars have to align.
We're still working through it.
I'll see you in Argentina
in a couple of days.
Going out of Coca-Cola,
I'm interested to play in La Fe.
I don't know,
I felt Louis is a really cool guy.
I'm still going to think about it,
but it's a really, really good option.
You'll look great in pink.
- Pink?
- Better than fucking red and white.
I could be fine with pink. Eh?
I like… It's not that bad.
Fuck yeah, baby. Let's go.
- Good job.
Before the U.S. Open final,
we are, uh, doing, um, a barbecue.
And Valiente and La Dolfina,
it's pretty much the same thing.
The same organization.
It's like the two Mercedes cars racing
in the last moment against each other.
It's not easy to be
in a final of the U.S. Open
against a dad.
It's going to be
an important moment for me.
I have to prove that I can win
a big tournament without my dad.
I like to play with a young kid,
but we are a young team,
and that is my future.
This new generation of players
makes the game incredible to watch.
I mean, when you see
what these guys can do
at 35 miles an hour, it's really stunning.
But the older generation still stands.
Like Adolfo, he's always trying to find
an excuse for him to try
to do better than everybody else.
It's probably the most emotional finals
that I've played in my life.
Because Bob is not there,
because of what happened,
and then I know that it's Poroto,
but I want to beat him.
I want to win.
For Bob.
He's my partner. He's my friend.
Bob is part of our family.
We started this competition
about three weeks ago with nine teams,
and now we're down to the final two.
Valiente will take on La Dolfina.
Hollywood better be taking notes
because this is the type of story you see
in blockbuster films.
And now in the season finale,
which Cambiaso will be walking away
with the coveted trophy?
Will it be Adolfo,
who's seeking his 10th U.S. Open title,
or will it be his son?
The question has been
for a long time, can the kid do it?
Can he beat the old man?
Is the son gonna be
the master, ultimately?
Is he gonna outride his father?
Adolfo Sr. has been the greatest
of the greatest for so many years,
versus a young player
who has learned from the best.
What that family has done
to give Poroto all of the tools
and the comfort and the pressure
in a way that is an advantage.
Don't give them space.
Drown them, drown them.
Leave them away from the ball.
That's where we're going to break them.
I try to support Poroto
and support my husband.
They both want it and they both need it.
And they are very ready for it.
If you mess with them,
they'll do whatever they want.
But it is key for us
to give ourselves time,
the only thing I would change
is how we defend.
We're gonna suffer.
It's gonna be very disputed.
They are going to overtake us.
It is going to be a very cool game.
With faith, play calmly and with faith.
We are going to break them.
My husband, he's going to retire soon.
To compete against
30-year-younger kids, it's not easy.
It's not easy
to play against your son,
but I don't want to give him anything.
It's hard for me,
because they keep asking,
"Whose side are you going to be on?"
They're pushing me a lot.
It's been a very good season,
but you know, it's too much.
Being the mother and the wife
of these two men, it's too much.
♪ And the rocket's red glare ♪
♪ The bombs bursting in air… ♪
What a beautiful setting here
for the 2024 U.S. Open Polo Championship.
Field number one,
U.S. Polo at the National Polo Center.
You are gonna see the finest that polo
has to offer here on display today.
Chukker number one
off and working.
Poroto picks the pace up.
Cambiaso off and working.
It's his father now in front.
The pair of Argentine flag helmets meet.
The old man looking for the bump,
the ride off. They get tangled up there.
The kid gets it back.
Finding Panelo.
Panelo.
Panelo going to the goal.
Can he do it? Panelo.
Unbelievable magic we're seeing
between these two players.
Poroto hits Tommy on the fly.
They draw first blood on the day.
Buckle up, folks.
It's only gonna get better from here.
This is the pinnacle of polo
in the United States.
Panelo breaks to goal.
Big hit. He's got Poroto on the move.
Poroto, that ball about 30 yards out.
Poroto. Reaches over on the near side.
Oh, what a save by Adolfo.
Right off the doorstep.
Penalty against the team in blue.
Penalty number two gonna be
taken by Paco de Narváez Jr.
We're tied up at one goal apiece here
in chukker number one.
I need you to close it
more to the four,
when he comes to me I can't move.
- Come on.
- Come on. Let's go guys.
Adolfo, it's up. And a score.
Tommy Panelo has the ball.
He winds up and sends it
through the pack and between the posts.
That'll tie it all
at two goals apiece.
Peke. Peke González. Panelo.
Tommy Panelo.
- This is as even as it gets.
- Yeah.
Valiente regains the lead.
Trying to work this one
to get one more point to tie this game.
Oh, what a play. Poroto Cambiaso.
Did he get it?
- He got it.
What a goal.
He fakes
the shot on purpose,
creates some space for himself.
I wonder where he learned that.
Mm-hmm.
Father against son right here.
All right, that bell's gonna end
the first half of the finals
of the U.S. Open Polo Championship.
They're close, anything can happen.
They need one chukker
to make a difference.
What more could you ask for?
This has truly been
a back-and-forth battle all day long.
Poroto is going toe-to-toe with his father
and keeping his team right in it.
It's key when we're all
involved the old man starts hitting him.
He's going to yell at you,
and the next time he yells…
They're going to yell at you,
even if you didn't do anything.
So try to slow down now.
Let him scream. But slow.
There you throw yourself
with the ball. Where are you?
What happens, Paquito, is that if you
go forward on the wrong side
you end up like this
and Poroto make you like that.
- I can't go back.
- Well, turn around.
Fasten your seatbelt,
because the U.S. Open final is coming down
to these last three chukkers.
It is anybody's game at this point.
Penalty will go
in favor of Valiente.
And De Narvaez puts it on through.
It's now Valiente on the lead, 6-5,
over La Dolfina.
Poroto, there's the warning bell.
Can they beat the clock?
As Poroto has the ball, they trail by one.
Can he get it down there in time?
Poroto. Poroto about 80 yards out.
Poroto flips the ball over
to Tommy Panelo.
- Clock is ticking down.
Panelo goes to goal.
Panelo. Panelo. Panelo.
I'm not sure if that's a buzzer beater
or not. I don't think so.
- No, it's not.
- He hit it a second time.
The goal will not count.
That'll end the chukker, 6-5.
Let's hear it for both teams.
It wasn't a goal, tell him.
He hit it before the bell.
It was a goal, dude.
Here comes Poroto
to pick up the pass.
Poroto Cambiaso, ridden off,
leaves the ball behind for Panelo.
Panelo sends a bomb downfield.
Coming in, Rufino Merlos.
Rufi. Rufi. Rufi, looking for pay dirt.
Oh, Adolfo backs that ball out of danger.
On the field, though,
it's turned here by Panelo.
Adolfo… He stopped it off the doorstep,
but not in time.
Flag man says it was over the line.
Adolfo comes back to challenge.
Apparently, the flag man thought
it was over the line.
Adolfo says, "No, I had it first."
So is it tied?
Is it not?
We'll find out.
The goal counts,
and we've got a tie game once again.
Adolfo with the ball.
He moves it back to the left right here.
Rufi comes in.
Rufi with a great little back shot.
That's gonna set up Panelo.
Panelo takes off right now.
Then Poroto comes in, takes the ball,
as Tommy will take them in.
Poroto going to the goal,
looking good right here and now.
Can he put his team on top?
Poroto. Poroto Cambiaso!
- What a goal right here.
Goal-aso.
That's gonna end
the chukker right there.
La Dolfina in the lead
for the first time today.
Both teams look incredibly tired,
but the final battle has yet to come.
What an epic conclusion to the U.S. Open.
Ball's in play.
The game's back underway.
First one there, it's Adolfo.
Adolfo Cambiaso leads the charge.
Adolfo, nice approach.
Adolfo's shot is going, going, going.
Poroto. He got there.
Poroto, unbelievable play.
Denying his dad that goal.
Paquito winds up and hits
the penalty two straight on through
and now makes the score
seven goals apiece on the board
here in the final chukker
of the U.S. Open final.
Can't get any better
than this, Tony.
Poroto on the backhand hits to Panelo.
Panelo in scoring position.
Panelo winds up.
Panelo's got it?! Yes, he does!
La Dolfina retakes the lead,
but with three minutes left,
Valiente can still turn the tables.
Let's see where this leads.
Adolfo Cambiaso. Adolfo.
Waiting for his players
to get in position.
Now Adolfo winds up, sends a bomb.
Peke Gonzalez runs up there.
So does Alejandro Aznar.
Aznar with a back shot,
a loose ball taken here by Panelo.
Panelo's got the play,
avoids the hook from Paquito.
Panelo still has the ball.
Tommy Panelo waits for it
to settle at the boards.
Flips it over for Poroto.
Poroto shoots the goal. The ball is going.
Rufino Merlos.
Rufino, Rufino, Rufino.
Unbelievable goal by Rufino Merlos
to put his team up by two,
9-7 now the score.
Panelo.
Valiente breaking down.
They can't respond.
Panelo!
Huge goal right there.
The three-goal lead should seal the deal.
Valiente tries to create one more chance,
but they don't have enough time.
La Dolfina will take the match.
Final score, 10-7.
La Dolfina has done it.
They have beat Valiente
for the second time in a row.
Oh, wow. Look at Poroto.
He just won the U.S. Open,
but instead of celebrating,
Poroto runs over to show
his support for Bob's family.
What a beautiful moment.
I told you I was going
to hit him hard today!
Come on! Come on!
Love you, Mama.
What an animal! Go!
Wow, what a thrill!
Fucking hell!
Congratulations,
old man, anyway.
For the fight you put up.
- It was even until the end.
- Yes. And then at the end.
- Then at the end.
- Yes, I don't know what it was.
We screwed up a little.
And now, the perpetual trophy,
United States,
the U.S. Polo Open Championship.
La Dolfina.
♪ Look all around
What a beautiful sight ♪
♪ As we're reaching
For the greatest heights ♪
♪ We're reaching
♪ It's what we're waiting for
It's what we're dreaming of… ♪
They say
the difficult thing is not to get there,
but to stay at the top.
I'm gonna try to be on the top
and as high as possible in the sport.
We're gonna probably watch Poroto
growing as a polo player
through his career.
I'm very proud of him
that, uh, he's his own.
He has his own way of playing polo,
and he showed the world
that Poroto is Poroto.
And I'll be honest with you, uh,
that night I was pissed.
Really pissed off.
That night I didn't celebrate,
but, uh, the next day
we noticed that what we did
was something that is not easy to do.
You're seeing
the most iconic player
to ever play this game passing the torch
and seeing his son compete against him.
No other sport has that.
When we first started playing
with Adolfo, Poroto was really little,
and I think my dad has helped
make decisions along the way
for Poroto that's allowed him to flourish.
And I think he's super proud of that.
I think he's been so proud
of, uh, the player that Poroto has become.
Adolfo, now that he's got
Poroto coming at him,
I think it's given him new life.
It's given him something
to fight for again.
But Poroto is looking
to make a legacy of his own.
I don't think I have
many more years to play.
I don't want to look back
because you get too emotional.
I just go forward.
I want him to retire up there,
you know, on the best level.
It's not that important for him,
but for me it is.
My thinking is, let's see.
I know that the day
that I feel that I'm done,
that I'm relaxed, that I don't care,
is the day that I'll have to say,
"Okay, stop doing this."
But this was our second year
not winning the U.S. Open,
so you get something inside
and it gets bigger and bigger.
That is that revenge,
getting back the trophy.
I'm still capable of playing
a good game and beat anybody.
You always have something to learn
and something good
to take out of the season.
I'm just gonna go back again
and keep on trying hard
and trying to improve.
I've been talking with Louis.
I hope if it's not this season,
the next one or whenever,
I can play together with Louis.
The end of Wellington
is always bittersweet.
We kind of go our separate ways after
and we really never know
what's gonna happen next.
But regardless, I'm always proud of him
and I was really proud of him this season.
And I'm also excited
for what's going to come next for him.
No! Fucking shit
of your fucking mother.
Losing is just…
it's fucking terrible.
Good game.
But, I'm looking forward
to this upcoming season.
I'm just gonna keep trying.
This is the nursery.
How far out are we?
It could happen any day now.
She's ready. I'm ready.
And now the room's ready.
I'll look forward
to having baby Alina
and Ames, you know,
on the sidelines cheering.
Pam, she's gonna do whatever she can
to win the U.S. Open.
We'll be there cheering her on.
Yeah. She supports me,
and I will do the same for her.
Polo's up there, but family first.
Being able to tell Alina one day
that I had you and a few months later
I played the Women's U.S. Open.
I don't know if I can.
We're gonna see how things play out.
But ultimately, that would be
a pretty wonderful experience.
Louis, Ames, Alina, and I
could make up a team one day
and play in a tournament.
It would be incredible.
We are a small organization
against the big boys.
And last year and the year before,
we never out-horsed.
We keep equal footing
and that's a big credit
to the team behind us.
And that's Timmy's horsemanship also.
We are very proud of that.
That's the man.
At the end, we were close,
but we were not close enough.
A loss is a loss. What did we learn?
We love each other.
That's 100%. We will get better together.
You little cookie monster.
Timmy is for sure a warrior.
He goes out there.
I know he has the ability
to make his own little polo legacy.
I know I can be great.
I just have to get there.
Maybe it's not today.
Maybe it's not winning the next U.S. Open.
But the goal is to win a U.S. Open.
I'm gonna bring it home one day.
♪ My dreams come alive ♪
Kids like Timmy, Keko, Poroto,
the younger generation,
they make things
that we wouldn't dream possible.
Time for the young kids.
The game has picked up in speed,
and the players
are much more athletic now.
You're going to see a higher skill,
a more fearless risk-taking
than you've ever seen before
in the next generation to come.
The beautiful thing is
that they all wake up and dream
that they're going to be
the next U.S. Open winner.
♪ My dreams come alive ♪
"Together, they fell fast asleep."