Since I've been playing polo,
I've broken both my ankles,
broke my jaw, my nose two times,
some fingers, broke my collarbone,
blew up my teeth, tore my left knee up.
If I could do it all over again,
I'd do it all over again.
What the hell just happened?
Why do people keep partaking in it?
People are absolutely in love with horses.
They're like the perfect balance
between elegance and power.
I don't know, you feel it.
You feel different. You feel you can fly.
Imagine going on a horse
at 30, 35 miles an hour
with someone coming at you at full speed.
There's a little bit of danger involved.
Polo's considered the second
most dangerous sport behind motor sports.
The trust between man
and animal is incredible.
It just gives you goosebumps sometimes
when you're watching the game,
to see them and how they're capable
of avoiding injury.
But when you're seeing a battle play out
at the highest goal level,
anything can happen at a moment's notice
that could end their careers
in a heartbeat.
Valiente.
One of the best teams in the tournament.
And we're gonna win it.
It should be good.
Against Clearwater,
we were on, we were on point,
the team was firing,
all of us were connecting.
We were doing our jobs.
We have to get back to that feeling
of that we're invincible
kind of ideology that we can do it,
'cause Valiente,
they're the best in the world.
It's always a pleasure to play against
the GOAT himself.
To beat Adolfo, don't get Adolfo angry.
If he gets pissed off,
he will score goals on you all day long.
Obviously, it's Adolfo Cambiaso.
He's the Michael Jordan of our sport,
or he's the GOAT.
I get to tell my kids
I played against the GOAT.
Now he's getting older,
you try to use that always
to your advantage.
I want to beat him.
That's… I want to beat him.
Timmy Dutta playing number one.
Since they switched their lineup
and they changed it up to this version,
the team has gone much better.
Adolfo, you can always tell it's him
with that Argentine flag helmet
he likes to sport.
Today is the day.
Last time we played them,
we went into overtime.
I was in the back. Now I'm in the front.
Tomas is back too for this game,
so… …score the goals.
That's all I gotta do.
Score the goals
so Tomas doesn't yell at me.
It'll be tough. This will probably be
one of our hardest games of the season.
Could be a sleeper team.
If they can win today,
man, I tell you what,
it could be a huge victory for them.
Penalty two.
Start off this second chukker.
Here comes Adolfo. Look at that.
It is up, and he drains it.
Right there. Gets his team on the board.
We got a 1-1 score on the board.
Adolfo is such a master of the game,
especially at this level
that it's really tough to bet against him.
Here comes a shot from Adolfo.
Two in a row for Cambiaso.
And that'll end the chukker.
He's taking matters
into his own hands,
and quickly back-to-back goals.
- Get on.
- Let's go.
Get on. Get on. Get on.
Timmy, focus.
They're throwing the ball in.
This is why
I don't need five people yelling.
He's almost 50 years old,
and he still plays… on a good day,
it's not even quantifiable.
Motherfucker.
- The intensity picking up.
- Blood's pumping.
Adolfo working his way around
to the inside of Joaquin Avendaño.
Here comes Obregon to try to get the hook.
Cambiaso gets rid of it just in time.
Ball pops loose here.
Picked up by De Narvaez.
Fight!
Get the ball!
We just had a…
a bit of a wreck here.
Ambulance!
The Valiente patron,
Bob Jornayvaz, went down.
We had a collision.
When Bob came down, he hit his head hard.
Hopefully, he's gonna be okay.
Horse is okay.
Bob's still being looked at.
- Hopefully he's all right.
- It's tragic.
The ambulance is coming,
and probably a helicopter.
- He got hit hard. Thank God, he…
- Everyone's traumatized.
He's breathing again.
He's breathing now.
At first he wasn't.
Stay where you are for now.
The ambulance will transport Mr. Jornayvaz
over to the trauma hawk
on the neighboring field.
You told them?
I called them. I go.
The second chukker comes.
There's, like, a minute
and twenty-five left. Bob falls.
Very bad fall. One of the worst ones
I've seen in a very long time.
You know, ambulance comes.
Helicopter comes.
Takes him to the hospital.
Family is everything.
We think of the team as a family.
We are a family.
When something like that happens,
it feels like a big shock. Like a…
It's a reality check.
- But they already took him?
- Yes.
I'm going to see if Robert
needs anything, poor thing.
- Robert is in there.
- They're asking him 300 questions.
This is the worst part
of polo. It takes any desire away.
Many things in my head,
uh, through that moment.
Bob, he's so special. He's a great guy.
He's like my father, a second father.
I… I don't know. It was hard for me.
Basically,
what we're hearing right now
is that neither team wishes
to continue with the game at this point.
And, um, we pray that he's gonna be okay.
Sergio.
I just heard from…
They said that Bob is in a coma.
Que… está stable.
- He hasn't gotten up yet.
- But stable?
But stable.
That's good news.
But he still has the brain hematomas.
That's gonna be tough, hey? To come back.
Think about it.
It's not a vehicle, not a car.
I have a 1,200-pound animal
underneath me I'm controlling with my legs
going flat out… into somebody else.
A whole bunch
of dangerous things can happen.
I just hope that Bob turns this around
and comes out of this okay,
and he's all right.
We're praying for his family,
for him, and for a fast recovery.
This game, it's so beautiful.
But it can go from
one of the most enjoyable moments
to a terrible moment really fast.
You kind of always
in the back of your mind say,
"That won't happen to me."
It won't happen to my dad.
And, um…
it does.
Yeah.
I might need one minute.
I never thought in a million years
it would happen to him.
But the one thing I do know is,
like, my dad's a fighter.
He fought his way to the top,
and he'll fight his way back to life.
Bob Jornayvaz is one of the…
biggest and most well-known patrons
in our sport.
He's put more money,
blood, sweat, tears,
everything into polo,
more so than just about anyone else.
Adolfo and Bob are
one of the greatest stories in polo.
And that part of the reason why
Adolfo's had so much success
is because he had the support of Bob.
There's a lot of
fantastic organizations,
but that one's different.
They've been at it the longest,
and they've been dedicated to excellence.
Bob's a friend of mine.
I just texted him and said,
"I just care about you."
And, "My family
and I'll be praying for you."
Even the rival teams,
rival players,
everybody puts all that aside.
And we all pull for Bob.
This tragic accident that
happened, these guys are big and tough,
but life is fragile.
I'm gonna dim the lights.
It's gonna be a little dark.
I'm gonna have you lay down
so you can get comfy.
Now that the season is done
for the La Fe team, my family's not here.
My friends have all left.
Being six months pregnant, it's not… easy.
It can feel a little bit isolating.
Hello, my love.
Hi, baby.
They're about to pull up her image
on the screen, so I wanted to call you.
Even though the U.S. Open
is over now for us,
I want to be able
to keep on getting better
so that I can elevate my game,
become a better player.
So I started traveling back and forth
to Argentina twice a week.
- I'm going…
- I'm not there.
- You what?
- I said, I'm sorry I'm not there.
Instead of the usual 12 to 15-hour days,
five, six days a week
that I normally put in,
thankfully I have a business partner
that's been, you know, running things.
Everybody kind of picked up the slack
and helped me out
to allow me to allocate
some time towards polo.
And then obviously Pam.
She's made a lot of sacrifices,
so I think it's just a group effort.
Oh, look at that little face. Hi.
She's so cute.
She has her tongue sticking out
a little bit as well.
Holy shit.
Oh!
For such a macho man,
I would have expected him
to want a little boy,
but no, he was dead set
on having a little girl.
The pink jerseys this season
was Louis' idea.
He was really excited to have a baby girl.
I wish I was there.
Robi… godfather.
Yes, but if he has one sassy thing to say…
She looks like me.
I have… spent
a lot of time away from my wife,
who would like to spend more time,
um, you know, with me.
Ooh, she just kicked.
Ooh.
She kicks hard.
Yeah, she does.
Baby, your little baby girl
is rather aggressive.
She gets that from you.
Sometimes what I want to say
is this is a hobby.
Louis' not a polo player.
He's a businessman
who does polo as a hobby.
If it were your lifeblood and career,
I can understand why
you need to dedicate that time.
I think his priorities right now
are different from mine.
It would be a lot better if I was there.
Yeah.
His time, I guess, is what I want. Time.
Now we have to drive
I think, like, five hours.
Four or five hours
to go play a tournament.
Very cool.
So, um…
There have been times where
it's definitely been difficult for me
during this pregnancy.
And especially now, um,
I just, I really want him to be here.
So I just, I need
to voice those feelings to Louis.
Tell the boys
over there I said hello.
- I will. Love you. Bye.
- Love you.
Love you.
- Bye, sweetie.
- Bye.
I hope that there's a shift.
I pray that there's a shift.
After Bob fell down,
it was a big deal for me.
You don't think about the game.
You don't think about anything but him.
We share our lives.
I know all his family,
and we were pretty much all together,
you know, praying for him
and… it was really hard.
I didn't know if I was able to keep going,
to keep playing.
I'm here because of him,
and he's my friend.
In the best moments of my career
or the worst moments of my career,
he was always there.
And I believe those are your friends.
Definitely, the accident
had a huge impact on Adolfo.
It's no question in anybody's mind, um,
who the greatest player
to ever play this game is.
That's Adolfo Cambiaso.
And, uh…
there's also no question who the best,
uh, sponsor of a team is, um…
over the course of his career,
and that's my father, Bob.
Adolfo's on Auna.
This is the mare that was named
after Bob's eldest daughter.
Adolfo's wearing the number one jersey
today in solidarity with Bob.
It also looks like a majority of the teams
have come to show support for Bob
and to support Valiente.
We are continuing
the Valiente versus Dutta Corp game today.
Three to two on the board,
the starting score in favor of Valiente.
And then Joaquin is playing
the number four position.
Joaquin Vilgre filling in.
We all wish Bob a speedy recovery,
and we've got nothing
but wonderful wishes.
Everybody's pulling for him.
Boys, let's get it done.
Let's do it, yeah?
It was really everything
kind of, uh, strange,
emotional, because Bob was not there.
But I think the courage of the family
gave me that enthusiasm
to keep going and play for him.
And that's what we did.
There's really no question about it
that my dad would want
this organization to keep going.
Show everybody exactly what they can do.
Ball's back in play.
Timmy trying to get this one
put between the posts.
Timmy out in front.
Come on, Timmy!
Reaches out near side.
Neck shot from Dutta.
Oh, man, off the post and goal.
- That's the way, Timmy.
What a goal, Timmy.
Coming in hot. Look at this.
Well done, Timmy. Oh, yeah.
What a play. Dutta-- Oh, man.
Adolfo comes in.
And Adolfo's gonna make him
pay for it here.
Wind up, fire at the goal from distance.
Cambiaso winds up,
cuts it at the goal.
Sends it on through.
What a goal by the master himself.
- Valiente back on top.
- Adolfo looks like he's hot.
Three goals, two assists for Adolfo.
Looking for a shot.
He likes what he sees.
Look at this shot from Del Rio.
Oh, what a play!
Yes!
Unbelievable!
Watch Timmy Dutta knock it down.
- Right to Nino.
- That was awesome.
An amazing goal like that
could be just what Dutta needs
to get back into this game.
Five minutes left on the clock.
Here we go.
Good effort here from
the Dutta Corp. Working this one down.
Here comes Nino firing at the goal,
and he drills it and picks up the point.
-
Now it's a ball game.
Running down the field,
Timmy comes in one time
at the goal from distance.
Over the back line wide.
- Still time for the Dutta Corp.
- Shit.
- That would've been a great…
- They needed that one.
A great time to score
to put the pressure on Valiente.
Adolfo comes back around behind.
Now back shot here
from Timmy to break out…
Look at this. No way.
What a goal. Timmy Dutta.
Yes!
Just what they need to have happen.
Timmy is a hero right now.
This is truly anybody's game now.
Bounces up,
and it's gonna be Adolfo to jump on it.
Taking this ball straight to goal.
It's hero time.
That clock is ticking down.
If Adolfo scores here,
that's pretty much game over.
Can't keep it alive.
15 seconds on the clock.
Oh, no! Dutta Corp stole possession.
Twelve seconds to go until the horn.
Can he make it happen right here
on this drive?
It'll come down to this.
Hits it one time down
the right-hand side of the field.
He's trying to get it to Dutta.
I was gone. I had that goal set up there.
I needed the 80-yard pass.
Ka-boom. Boom.
Went 60.
It's not gonna have
enough power on it.
Killed me,
that that pass was short. Ugh.
But, um… I had the opportunity.
That's gonna win
the game for Valiente.
Unbelievable.
What a game. What a showing here.
Congratulations, Valiente.
They will take home the win,
9-8 the score.
That's gonna be a tough loss,
but they can hold their heads high against
this incredible Valiente team
that gets it done.
We went toe-to-toe,
to even have a chance
to go into overtime with them.
When you lose by one,
we were pissed, to be honest with you.
It was one of those small, fine lines.
It could've gone either way.
Now we have Pilot coming up,
and we have to win no matter what.
You have to win
to keep us in the rest of the tournament.
But it's not over yet.
With that loss, Dutta Corp
finds themself in a must-win position.
One more loss,
and they are out of contention
for the semifinals.
We have a game tomorrow
against Dutta Corporation,
and they're playing very strong right now.
Uh, the last game
that Dutta played against Valiente
we're gonna have to have
a really good game to beat them.
I feel like we can,
but what they all don't have
is a player like Facundo.
With him, you're always the team to beat.
When he's having a good day,
he can win it all by himself.
Facundo and Adolfo have been trading
the number one and number two position
for the last… you know, 20 seasons.
That's why there's a kind of like mission
to beat the other guy,
because they have always been the…
Who's the best player in the world?
Is it Adolfo? Is it Facundo?
I've been a polo player
nearly since I was born.
I have a family that is all polo players.
My father, my brothers, my uncles,
all my cousins were all polo players.
When I started playing
as a professional polo player,
I wanted to be as better as I could be,
and I'm constantly looking for that.
Facundo Pieres,
he flicks it in towards the goal!
Facundo's one
of the great players.
He's been at the top
of the game for many years.
He's won all the big tournaments.
The word for him is unstoppable.
What you feel when you're playing
is that you have
this like bullet train coming,
and, you know, you better hope that he…
something happens and he misses the ball,
because he's not someone
you'll be able to stop.
It's another magical goal
from the ten-goal maestro…
I've been playing
with Facundo now for five years.
In my opinion, he's the best pro
that ever played the game.
You give him the ball, and he's gone.
Facundo! Facundo! Facundo!
Of course, I had
all my career playing against Adolfo.
There's been a big rivalry
for a long time
between Cambiaso and Facundo Pieres.
Facundo is
the number one in the world
because he's taking
the podium away from Adolfo Cambiaso.
The skill, he's at the right age.
I have no question about it
there's some type of rivalry on the field.
That's where I actually hope
we get to a point in the Open
where we're having
those both on the same field
and playing against each other.
Seeing that level of play
would be so incredible to watch.
Life for everybody changes
and now I have different priorities.
So what colors
do you want to use?
I always knew
that I wanted to have kids.
They changed my life, for sure.
What do I do every day?
- What do I do the most?
- Play polo!
- And do you sometimes come to watch me?
- Sometimes.
- And do you enjoy watching me?
- No!
They live in Argentina,
and I travel, so they come to visit me.
A couple of years ago,
I got into a divorce.
Outside my polo career,
that was my biggest failure as a person.
You know, like,
something went wrong there.
How delicious.
Do you want a drumstick?
Okay.
Do you want to stay or leave?
I want to stay.
A few more days?
I don't get to see them
as much as I want.
But when I see them, I spend a lot of time
with them. Good quality time.
I've been struggling
a bit in a couple of years,
but now everything looks
to be a little bit more balanced,
so I have my head more ready to go
and concentrate in my game.
If there's one team in the world
that you can put at the level
of Valiente and La Dolfina, it's Pilot.
They won the U.S. Open,
you know, three or four times already.
Curtis is someone that also understands
the power of horses.
Curtis is the person
that has been spending the most,
and obviously having Facundo
is always an edge,
which makes, you know,
Pilot always one of the teams to beat.
I had a lower disc hernia
at the beginning of the season.
I never had that injury before,
and now I have to take care
of all the rest of my body
because having that pain
made my body restructure a little bit.
It's not easy to do that.
It's very difficult.
Timmy Dutta, he's playing forward now.
I think probably that's one of the reasons
why the team is doing better now.
I think he's at his best.
- Come again?
- Does that scare you?
Yeah, I mean, respect.
I don't know if scared, but respect.
Dutta.
They're coming on strong right now.
Their lowest goal player
with a handicap is four,
so if you're under four goals,
you gotta have a very good game
for your team to win.
Now Dutta is going a lot forward, so…
What I've seen is
we're gonna have to go in with Avendaño,
not with Timmy.
Okay.
Because Timmy is fast.
Timmy, what a play right here.
Dutta in the red zone.
Another one.
Dutta jumps out of here
and goes with it right now out in front.
Can he get to it?
Yes, he does.
Man, oh, man.
He's had some fantastic finishes.
But if it is with Joaquin Avendaño,
it's different. I think you can do it.
With Timmy Dutta, he will be very fast.
So we're going to defend a lot.
If I don't at least try to take Timmy
and try to get in his way,
then there's going to be a free man
who you can score any time.
We don't smile
until after the game tomorrow, right?
How depressing it is
to drive over to this place
now that the season is over.
Yeah? But we still have horses here,
so it's not that depressing.
- It is for me.
- When are you going to Argentina?
I'm going…
tomorrow.
And when do you come back?
I don't know.
Okay.
We started a breeding operation
with Robi down in Argentina,
which is actually where most of our…
um, like, our finances
and our capital is allocated to that.
And obviously, you know,
winning is important,
because if we don't win, then,
you know, we don't showcase
the horses as much.
If we don't perform well,
then it's money that's not well spent.
I'm gonna spend Greek Easter
with my family.
- Okay.
- If you can make it, I would love it.
I will fly back if I'm not playing.
Perfect.
Perfect… As in, like, perfect? Or…
Perfect as in, it would be great
to have you there if you could make it.
But if you can't make it,
because there's something
more important, then that's okay.
It's rare for her to…
to manifest her feelings.
And when she does, you know,
I pay really close attention to it.
I wanna make sure
that polo doesn't become all-consuming.
It's not like this season's been…
you know, that exciting.
I spent a lot of our financial resources
into what I think is a very…
disappointing season.
We should find excitement and enjoyment
in more than just winning.
You mean in… in us?
As long as I know that you know
your priorities, I'll always support.
I do know my priorities, yes.
So as long as it doesn't get
too far off base and too skewed,
I'll always support it.
Understood.
I'll always support you.
Okay.
Is that an, "Please stop telling me that,"
or is that an okay?
There has not been a day that's gone by
where I don't think about we could've
spent more time together.
And I'm sure it can feel really lonely,
and I'm sorry for that.
- I love you, thank you.
- I love you.
I hear you.
You happy?
- Right now, this second?
- Mm-hmm.
I'm very happy.
It's one of these games
that's like, all the pressure is on you.
It's the game that is
the game of the games, right?
It's that one last showdown that,
I mean, if we win against Pilot,
it gives us a shot in the semis.
And, uh, hey, Facundo Pieres…
He is the man.
He's a top dog.
He's the team to beat, though.
It's the team to beat. We'll beat them.
We'll beat them.
Very important,
that as soon as we have the ball today,
you are ready, eh?
You have to give Facundo.
If you stretch the team
as soon as we have it,
you put him in a difficult position,
you know?
I was there at the hospital
and they came out with good news.
Said he was going to be fine and all that.
And then it all went to shit.
So.
- Is his wife there with the kids?
Yeah.
- We met her there at the hospital.
So Louisa is here.
Yeah. So.
It didn't have to be.
No. It's… it's polo.
- I mean, things move fast.
- Yeah.
And us, not you,
but us old people, us being me.
- Hey, I'm 58.
- Yeah, but I'm 65.
- Good luck, my friend.
- Good luck.
- You too. Will do.
- Have fun.
- Take it easy on the old man.
- Yeah.
- Good to see you, young man.
- Good luck.
- Thank y'all.
Five out. Let's go. Get it done.
Good luck, huh?
Thank you, sir.
Think, focus. Today is your day to shine.
Go.
You can do it.
The main thing today,
Timmy Dutta never has a free run to goal.
And he's well mounted.
You say with the Dutta Corp,
they've gotta win.
- They have to.
- They've gotta beat them.
Ball's put into play.
Facundo goes to the ball.
He takes off with it.
Oh, man, it got away from him.
Won't see that too often.
Here comes Facundo.
Penalty number two. Oh, no.
First miss of the season.
Facundo started off the game
a bit slower than he normally does.
When we saw him miss the first penalty,
maybe we found a crack and can get in.
And then watch
this cut shot from Facundo.
Look at this. Oh, man.
He overcut it.
I guess it just goes to prove
he actually is human.
Facundo's a power polo player,
I like to say.
He's gonna run through you and score.
Here's Facundo.
Look at this horse just explode for him.
Takes his shot. Facundo… finds the goal.
Sends it on through.
Goal by Facundo, his first of the day.
Making up
for that penalty two miss, Facundo.
- Facundo there is challenged.
- Shit.
Taps it out. Bounces it up.
Keeps it going right here.
Winds up. Cuts it at the goal.
Look at this. Oh, man.
What a shot. Unbelievable.
- Facundo breaks back to the center.
- Shit.
Facundo will not miss.
Sends it through.
Picks up the point and extends his lead.
-
We can't let this
get any more out of control.
He's bringing her back. What for?
He needs to stay there.
Timmy, it's not chukker end.
- The fucking horse is dead, Tim.
- I know.
Let the horse breathe.
Let me get on the next mare.
Let her breathe.
We haven't seen
Timmy find the scoresheet.
True.
Timmy trying to come on strong
from behind.
Curtis Pilot coming back
to defend against Timmy Dutta.
Great job
by Curtis taking out Timmy.
Not letting Timmy jump on that right away.
Well done, Curtis.
What a play, Curtis Pilot.
Timmy comes in for the steal.
Takes it away.
Dutta is gone on a break
as Facundo tried to pick up
the right-of-way.
It's gonna be taken by Dutta,
looking to put one on the board.
Can he get it done? Timmy.
There's Curtis. Gets to it.
Well done, Curtis.
Four goals down. One chukker left.
It's gonna be very difficult
for the Dutta Corporation
to get anything done.
Try to score as quickly as possible.
- Maybe draw a foul.
- Yeah.
Nice angle put together there
for Dutta on the near side.
Timmy Dutta. It's off the post. Oh, baby.
And that will take us
out of chukker number five.
We're down
to the final chukker and now
Dutta Corp is in desperation mode.
If they can't pull out the win,
they will be eliminated.
I know why they call this
a young man's sport. Son of a bitch.
We need some goals.
Had to hit the fucking post.
Looks like a possession play.
Tomas hits it straight at the goal.
Centers it up for Nino.
And now Del Rio smack it through the goal.
What a goal for the Dutta Corporation.
Back within two now. 7-5 the score.
They're there.
We have time.
- Less than a minute remaining.
- Del Rio gives that ball a big run.
- They've gotta score now.
- Yeah, they have to burst down.
Just try to go score.
Hopefully you get lucky.
Taking too much time.
You gotta shoot
if you want to have a chance.
Del Rio's back to it.
Tomas Garcia Del Rio.
Hit the fucking ball, guys.
Come on. Who's got it?
Taken now by Del Rio.
Del Rio knows he needs to shoot.
Can he get it done? Del Rio coming in.
Del Rio runs it on through.
Picks up the point,
brings the team within one.
There is still time, especially if--
- The horn went before he scored.
- Oh, did it go?
- That's a shame. That's game.
- He tapped it.
Seven to six, the final on the scoreboard.
Congratulations, Pilot,
here on the Open match.
That is it, officially.
Man, so close,
but they weren't fast enough.
This means the Dutta Corporation
has been eliminated from the U.S. Open.
Good job, Timmy.
They gave it all.
- That's all you can ask.
- So proud of you.
Great job. We tried hard.
I know you wanted it so bad.
Be proud of yourselves,
though, in a lot of ways,
because these are big organizations.
I think he's gonna question
every single goal he didn't score
and how he could have just turned
his wrist just the slightest way
and, you know, probably all day long.
Another year.
Another roller coaster.
This young man
has such a bright future.
Nearly taking down two giants of the sport
in back-to-back games,
Adolfo and Facundo. But not today.
Instead, we'll have to wait
for those giants to collide.
Cloves, cardamom.
Who's gonna chop?
Am I chopping or you're chopping?
- Or you're looking pretty?
- I can do anything.
I got it. Make me a drink.
I keep saying it over and over,
and I feel like a broken record,
but it's such-- It was a fine line
of winning and losing always.
We lost games so close.
We lost by one, two, one, two. We lost.
- Yeah.
- And being very close to beat them.
We had an incredible defense that
the big boys just couldn't penetrate us.
Against the biggest of the biggest boys,
and that's all we could ask for.
That small margin.
Can you take this
and start chopping?
- Just the tips? Okay.
- Yeah.
When you play these ten-goalers,
they have so much talent
and depth of horses,
uh, that we make a mistake, it's a goal.
- We learn from them.
- Yeah.
Would it be amazing
to beat Mr. Cambiaso?
Absolutely, 100%.
It would be an honor and a dream,
and the guys…
I think you learn more from him,
playing him, and Facundo Pieres,
because they're the best in the world,
and if we don't, we're stupid.
It's a fact.
One day, I hope we win the U.S. Open.
I hope it's next year.
You have to start dreaming
to beat the big boys.
I've dreamed of that cup. That's for sure.
Now I'm gonna build the biryani.
- Is it looking good?
- Yeah. It's cooked.
He has got a huge future
ahead of him as a polo player.
- Want me to get a serving spoon for that?
Yeah.
He has four shots as a polo player
as good as any ten-goal player.
Looks good.
He can reach anyone at 140 yards
to their stirrups, which not many
sitting ten-goal players can do that.
That's just a fact.
Timmy started the Open at one level,
and he finished at a different level.
And that's winning to me.
A little pickle, a little chutney.
So if he plays simple polo,
it's hard to beat him.
I'm not worried about it.
Before 30, he'll be there.
And he's just… he's extremely bright.
Uh, I wouldn't comment on the way
he looks, but he has a great personality,
and he's just an amazing kid.
He makes me proud every day.
He's the greatest joy I have,
and thus I say,
I'm a very rich man because of him.
It's not the money in the bank
or what I own or et cetera.
It's him. It's very simple.
I love you and appreciate
everything you do.
I love you too.
I'm so proud of you. Well done.
- Great season.
- Thank you so much.
Thank you. I really appreciate it.
- My goodness, the damn thing is good. Mm.
- It's so good.
We're back
with one of our final games
of bracket play
before we get to the semifinals,
Valiente will take on Coca-Cola.
With each team playing
four games in bracket play,
three wins guarantees
a trip to the semifinals.
Valiente and La Dolfina
have both secured their spots,
so two more are still up for grabs.
Any team that has lost three games
are now out of the running,
meaning that Dutta Corp,
La Fe, and Clearwater
are out of contention.
Pilot, Park Place, Coca-Cola, and Tamera
all have one more game to go
and all looking
for a spot in the semifinals.
If they lose today,
Coca-Cola will be out of the U.S. Open.
He's under a tremendous amount
of pressure, Keko is.
To be really young
and to continue to perform
better and better
every time he goes on the field,
I can't imagine what kind
of pressure he's dealing with.
Today is a really special day,
not because of polo,
because it's Keko and I's
one-year anniversary of dating.
So, no matter how it goes,
he's going to be in a good mood later
when it's me-time
and time for us to celebrate.
Hopefully, he'll be happy
regardless of how this goes.
With three wins under their belt,
Adolfo's undefeated Valiente team
are already through to the semis,
but the men feel the absence
of their sponsor, Bob Jornayvaz.
Our hearts go out to him and his family.
How is he?
He's not very good, Harry. He's in a coma.
I think it's just going to be a long haul.
Yeah, so.
- They're trying to get him to wake up.
Trying to wake up now.
That's the idea right now. So.
Good luck.
Yeah, so, I've got
Adolfo and Robertito going down tonight
to say any kind
of stimulation and talking.
Things like that.
He's gonna listen to the game.
- Yes. And he loves to… Bueno.
- It's wonderful to see you.
- Everything's gonna be okay.
Yes. We're thinking about you.
Thanks, Harry.
That means a lot. Thank you both.
The best thing to do now
is to win the whole tournament.
Yeah, I think you're right.
If you wanted to get
the opportunity to be in the semis,
it's a must-win, yeah, 100%.
So, of course, the intensity is high.
I just put the pressure on myself.
Polito,
he's been fantastic this entire season.
Really, Toby,
they have to all play extremely well.
We know they play best when they play
a good team-style hit-and-run.
Coca-Cola, Valiente,
just about ready to go head-to-head here.
Ball's in play.
Cambiaso's moving through the pack.
Oh, baby, look at that.
How does this happen?
Adolfo should not be this alone,
by himself, going to the goal,
picking up the first point,
making the score 1-0.
What a shot from Paquito.
Look at this play.
Does it have the legs
to get across the line?
Beautifully done there.
Peke off and running.
Look at this.
What a shot from Peke. 3-0 now the score.
They are off to the races early.
Coca-Cola, again,
they need to win this game.
Let's see if they can turn this around.
For Valiente, the thrill of,
"If I lose, I'm out," is not there.
You know that you're in no matter what,
so you're relaxed. You're focused,
but you're relaxed.
Versus the other team, it's tight.
If we win, maybe we have a chance,
and you're a little tighter,
'cause if you don't win,
then you're out for sure.
This is the U.S. Open, come on.
Let's play well.
- Let's play.
- Let's go.
Concentrate, talk to me, talk to me.
Keko.
Wins a throw-in.
Magrini catches the top of that one.
screaming in Spanish]
Let's go! Dude.
Backed up by… Ruiz.
Ruiz with a little flip-neck shot
at the goal,
and he will send it on through.
Keko Magrini.
Oh, a little slip-up.
Now,
Polito Pieres taking control now.
Keko's got to prove
that he's still got it, that he's there.
That he should be there.
Polito likes what he sees.
He'll shoot at the goal.
He went for the big shot.
And this one will go. What a goal!
- Yes, he nailed it.
- Yes.
Incredible goal there
from Polito Pieres.
And ties this game up
now at three goals apiece.
It's gonna be picked up by Peke,
who got there first.
And now Keko comes in to challenge.
Gonzalez has an inbound
Keko Magrini to deal with.
He gets the shot off. Oh, man.
Tough break there for Keko.
Look. Here comes Keko.
Got his mallet all tangled up.
Couldn't get to it.
Taken here by Joaquin Vilgre.
And Vilgre got it done.
Sends it on through.
Breaks a tie. Takes the lead
and makes the score 5-4.
Tough for Keko Magrini so far.
And you can see there's some words
being said between Polito and Keko now.
Kind of butting heads a bit at this point.
Polito is not happy.
Because you
are looking at me but tell me yes or no.
Think!
Let's go, come on!
- Are you looking at me?
- Yes, I get it.
Yes, or you don't understand?
Listen to me, Keko.
Get him, dude. Come on!
Okay, okay.
This is so bad, man.
Okay!
- Be more conservative with the ball.
- Okay.
This game is important
for me to show the team what I can do.
But I still didn't feel really good.
I don't know.
I was putting
too much pressure on myself.
And I felt the things were not going
really good my way this season.
And I was just probably
mad at myself more than anything.
Polito and Keko's styles
are similar.
They're both good with the ball.
Uh, they both like to have the ball.
We cannot argue about Keko's talent,
but Polito is a better player than Keko.
Keko needs to understand
that he's not going to be the guy
that stands out.
It became personal
between Polito and Keko.
Keko is very young.
I get quite angry.
And some days you need
that craziness to win big games.
Keko Magrini.
A beautiful pass from Keko Magrini
to Polito Pieres all by himself.
He'll wind up, shoot,
and send it on through
and pick up another point now
to make the score 8-6.
Coca-Cola, can they cling
to that two-goal lead here?
Running towards the goal.
Can he put it through here?
Victorino Ruiz over the back line wide.
But we're down to the last 30 seconds.
The 30-second bell is going to sound.
That means
a guaranteed victory for Coca-Cola.
They've got a chance to go to the semis.
Keko is super talented,
but I feel like it was
difficult for him to adjust
to having a player
like Polito on the field.
And Keko has been having trouble
figuring out his role on this team
with Polito.
Despite their rocky start
at the top of the competition,
Coca-Cola will survive
and have a chance
to make it to the semifinals.
- Should we go out tonight?
- No.
- Why not?
- Because.
Yes, please, thank you. So.
Tell him why not.
- What do you mean?
- Because we have plans.
- Yeah, but after.
- No, we spend the night together.
- Out.
- No.
- You don't want to go out.
- Why not?
- Because I don't want to.
We have dinner and we have plans.
You have a romantic night, right?
- Apparently.
- Yeah?
- I really want to…
- Okay, I'm going to cancel our dinner.
- And I'll go with Zach instead.
- Cool.
Okay. And you're good with that?
- Okay, I'm gonna go. Home.
- Where are you going? Why?
- Because I don't wanna be here.
- Why?
Like, time after the game,
that short of a time
you're still with the energy of the game,
with everything, and maybe if you're mad,
it's not a good moment.
The game itself
is incredibly competitive.
It isn't a surprise that
when you kind of crank it up to 11,
people can't hold on.
And, you know, my dad worked really hard
on building the absolute pinnacle
of excellence in this sport.
As my dad used to say a lot, he said,
"The lucky truck backed up
and dumped on him."
We're taking every single little win
that we can with my dad.
But sorrow and trauma, like, it has no,
it doesn't care who you are,
it'll come for you.
It's amazing how much, like, a little
squeeze of the finger means these days,
and open…
to open your eyes and have
a semblance of a smile
or something like that. It's like…
But yeah, to be honest,
all the little wins are…
absolutely…
They're the most exciting thing
in my world these days, honestly.
The other day, my mom kissed him,
and you could see his lips move.
It's like…
you know,
it just goes to show
there's so many things in the world
to be excited about
and all that stuff, but like,
when it really comes down to it,
like a kiss from your wife
when you're in that space, like,
is unbelievable.
You can count on one hand
the amount of people who matter,
really, really matter to you.
Life is a lot of sorrow,
but it's filled with a lot of joy.
We're hoping and praying
that it keeps going that way.