The train now
arriving on Platform 1
is the 5:30 from Ilfracombe,
Barnstaple, Exeter, and Yeovil.
The train now arriving
on Platform 1
is the 5:30 from Ilfracombe,
Barnstaple, Exeter, and Yeovil.
Good evening, Countess.
It's an honor to have you
with us again.
Your usual suite is ready.
Thank you.
Thank you, Countess.
Doesn't the town look good
at this time of year, Poirot?
Yes, one can always tell
when the summer, it is arrived.
It's in the air, eh?
No, Hastings, it is in the speed
of your driving.
Come on, Poirot,
we're only pushing 30.
Sorry, old chap.
Red light.
I prefer the winter.
It is safer.
Now, there's a pleasant sight
for you on a summer's day.
You ever thought about it?
In my experience,
I have known of five cases
of women murdered
by their devoted husbands.
Yes?
And 22 husbands murdered
by their devoted wives.
So, thank you, no.
The marriage,
it is not for me, ah?
And now I think the light,
it is green.
We can proceed -- gently.
Righto.
But I'm not
going to have a crash.
Anyway, we saw a bride.
That's supposed to be good luck.
Mr. Poirot, you're back.
The chief inspector's
waiting inside.
Chief Inspector Japp?
Here?
That must be the luck of which
you speak, Hastings.
I think he's worried
about something.
He hasn't said a word.
Chief Inspector.
Good afternoon, Poirot.
Captain Hastings.
Chief Inspector.
Please, seat yourself.
What matter is it
that brings you here today?
The matter of my job,
if you want the honest truth.
They'd never dismiss you,
would they, Chief Inspector?
They will if I don't get results
soon, Captain Hastings.
Three robberies
in as many weeks.
Jewelry each time.
The Atterton diamonds
were the first to go.
Lady Atterton?
In the West Country?
Happened during dinner.
Two dukes, a duchess,
and some Russian countess
around the table.
Not your usual run of witnesses.
They're high society.
Can't get much higher.
That's the trouble.
The commissioner's
come down on me.
He wants action.
If not, he's going to have to
give them a scapegoat.
A goat?
Me.
When was this last robbery?
Three days ago.
Three days?
But it is too late.
It is better to strike
while the metal is warm, yes?
So what can we do?
We wait.
Already the thief,
he is planning his next crime.
The next crime,
it will be his last.
This way, Countess.
Lady Runcorn.
How good of you to come.
And how exquisite you look.
Your parties are always
an experience, Marcus.
And tonight is no exception.
We have Nacora the pianist
playing for us.
And you know Katherine Bird.
The contralto?
My dear Marcus, one can't get
tickets to hear her
for love or money.
No need for either.
Oh, let me introduce you
to a colleague of mine
from South Africa.
Martin Johnstone, Lady Runcorn.
How do you do?
Excuse me.
Are you also a collector,
Mr. Johnstone?
What?
Jewelry.
Mr. Hardman has one of the
finest collections in England.
Is Lady Runcorn here?
Yes, I was just talking to her.
Oh, good!
She's quite attractive, really.
I wonder if she misses
the late Lord Runcorn.
For heaven's sake,
do try to be discreet.
You know me, Marcus.
Yes.
Who's that?
Countess Vera Rossakoff.
She came over from Russia
quite recently.
Yes.
I suggest you keep your hands
off of her, my dear boy.
Why?
You're not in her league.
I wonder.
And where have you been?
Busy.
Have you seen my gloves?
No, I haven't.
You couldn't ask
for the trail
to be much fresher
this time, Poirot.
I only heard myself
this morning.
I've been chasing
all over the country
on the other three robberies.
This is the first one
that's been close to London.
Tell me about
this M. Marcus Hardman.
He's a jewelry collector.
Something of a celebrity
in his own way.
Throws a lot of parties,
that sort of thing.
A collector, do you say?
Yes.
Natural target, I suppose.
And yet, in other circumstances,
perhaps also
the natural suspect.
They were in the garden
when it happened.
Some sort of concert.
In the garden?
There's a marquee.
Sir.
You were the constable
on duty last night?
Yes, sir.
Tell us what happened, then.
I was on my beat, sir.
I walked past Mr. Hardman's
house about half past 10:00.
And?
Well, sir, I did see something.
A vagrant.
He was going the other way.
Down there.
That vagrant could have had a
£10,000 necklace in his pocket.
I wasn't to know, sir.
Indeed not.
Thank you, Officer.
You've been most assiduous
in your duties.
It's a ghastly thing.
Just ghastly.
I mean, the publicity
will destroy me.
When did you notice
that the jewelry was absent,
M. Hardman?
It was this morning.
I got up late
after last night's concert.
We had Nacora play,
and Katherine Bird.
I came into the room --
my beautiful emerald necklace.
But it is insured, Mr. Hardman?
-Insured?
-Is it?
Well, of course it's insured!
That's not the point.
It's irreplaceable.
It used to belong to
Catherine de Medici, you know.
It's through here.
M. Hardman?
This window,
it is kept locked, yes?
Of course.
I'll show you the safe.
What's different
about this window?
It looks just like
all the others.
But there is one significant
difference, mon ami.
It is at this point
the climbing plant outside
almost reaches the sill.
And M. Hardman is, I think,
a little overconfident
about the latches.
Has anything been touched?
No, Chief Inspector.
This is just how it was
when I came in.
The safe was open,
and the emeralds were gone.
So what's this, then?
Is this yours, Mr. Hardman?
No.
What do you make of this,
Poirot?
It is a glove of a man --
a man with small hands.
What have we here?
Cigarette case.
Empty.
With the initials B.P.
B.P.
Is that of any significance
to you, M. Hardman?
Well, yes, I suppose it could
belong to Bernard Parker.
And who is he, sir?
Young friend of mine.
Uh, a business associate.
The glove could be his, too.
What makes you say that?
Well, he'd lost it.
He'd lost both his gloves.
At least, that's what he said.
Excuse me.
So what do you think, Poirot?
I think that it is strange.
The glove and the cigarette
case, it is,
as you might say,
the double clue.
Twice as much for us to work on.
It is too much, Hastings,
too much.
To leave the glove
inside the safe...
Perhaps he was in a hurry.
Someone could have
disturbed him.
Poirot?
May I introduce you?
This is
the Countess Vera Rossakoff.
She was here at the party
last night.
Enchanté, madame.
Et moi aussi, monsieur.
Hercule Poirot at your service,
madame.
What beautiful gardens,
M. Poirot.
It is so good of you
to escort me.
I wanted to bring you somewhere
that was worthy of you.
You mustn't flatter me,
M. Poirot.
You will make me cry.
I have been so lonely
since I arrived,
and it's been a lovely day.
Yes. I also know what it is
to come to a new country
and to know no one.
Of course.
You yourself are a refugee.
Yes.
I was head of the police
in Belgium.
But then came the Great War.
I was forced to leave.
I came to England -- to
the village of Styles St. Mary.
But it was a sad and painful
time for me --
so far from my family
and my home.
Poor M. Poirot.
Oh, no, I have had
a good fortune.
My talent,
it has been recognized.
It is reported that I am
the most famous detective
in England.
Is Poirot here?
No, actually not.
-Hastings?
-Yes.
Excuse me.
Where is he?
You all right, Chief Inspector?
No.
I'm not all right.
I'll be lucky
to be chief inspector
by the end of the week.
As bad as that, eh?
It's been three days,
Captain Hastings.
Three days, and nothing!
Well, Poirot is on the case,
you know.
Then why aren't you with him?
I don't know.
I suppose he wanted to pursue
his own line of inquiry.
This jewelry business
is going to be the end of me.
Don't worry, old chap.
You know Poirot.
He really is getting somewhere?
Oh, yes, I'm sure he's
on the right track.
And so you are investigating
the case of the stolen jewelry?
It seems a simple matter,
madame.
To England's most famous
detective, of course.
Do you suspect me?
Ha!
Should I?
I was there.
That is true.
So, tell me, madame, why did you
return the following day?
I had an appointment
with Mr. Hardman.
I was considering selling
some of my own jewelry.
I had a house like this
once in Petrograd.
First the house.
Then a wing in the house.
Then a room in the wing.
And now nothing.
But that does not make you
the thief, madame.
No.
Life itself is the thief.
It has taken everything I had.
Well, I suppose it had to happen
one day.
He's really quite taken,
you know.
Are you sure, Captain Hastings?
You should have seen him.
Well, anyway, we haven't seen
him, not for three days.
That's not like him.
What about poor old Japp?
Looks like he could be
for the chop.
If only we could help.
Maybe we can.
How?
Look, according
to Marcus Hardman,
only four people went into
the house during the concert.
That's when the jewels
were taken.
Bernard Parker,
Martin Johnstone,
Lady Runcorn,
and the countess.
Suppose it was her!
No, it can't have been her.
I mean, I hope to God it wasn't.
So what can we do?
Well, we can talk
to the other three
and solve the case ourselves.
I know old Japp suspects that
tramp the constable spotted,
but I think we should speak
to them all,
starting with Mr. Johnstone.
How dare you, sir?
If I want a jewel necklace,
I can afford to go into a shop
and buy one!
In fact, I can afford
to buy the shop.
So why did you go back
into the house, Mr. Johnstone?
The call of nature,
if you must know.
Were there any witnesses?
So, Lady Runcorn,
you don't deny that you went
back into the house.
But I just told you that,
Captain Hastings.
Hmm.
Did you see anyone else inside?
Yes, there was someone coming
out of the downstairs bathroom.
But I didn't see who it was.
Why were you in the house,
Lady Runcorn?
I went to fetch my handbag.
I'd left it inside.
Eh bien, Countess.
Tomorrow I will take you
to the Tate Gallery
to see their collection
of the Turners.
But I find these expressionist
painters so exciting.
Don't you, Hercule?
In part, yes.
Do you know, I do not believe
that there is anyone
of my acquaintance
who calls me by that name.
Oh.
I am so sorry.
Excuse me.
Madame.
Now, this I find most pleasing.
Marc Chagall.
Another Russian in exile.
He lives in Paris, I believe.
A constructivist, they call him.
But one only has to look
at his work to see --
Yes?
He is still in Russia.
He never left.
Like you, Countess.
Oh, no.
It's another world now.
Stalin, Hitler.
Everywhere you look,
it's all changing.
Goodbye, Lady Runcorn.
Goodbye, Captain Hastings.
Captain Hastings, look.
"B.P."
Bernard Parker!
Yes, I do some work
for Marcus --
Mr. Hardman.
I arrange his more
insalubrious deals.
What do you mean by that?
When the client doesn't
want his or her name
dragged through the mud,
I act as a sort of...
go-between.
I don't --
In high society, Captain,
nobody is ever hard up.
At least,
they don't admit to it.
So when they are hard up,
they come to me.
And I go to Marcus.
Have you lost a glove,
Mr. Parker?
Oh, the glove.
That simply loathsome
Inspector Snapp
has already been on to me
about the glove.
Do you know
he wanted to arrest me?
Was it yours?
Yes,
but I've told him, I had both my
gloves when the concert began,
and that was the last time
I saw them.
And as for the cigarette case,
I've never seen it before
in my life.
It had your initials.
Oh, my dear, I'm sure you'll
find plenty of people in London
with the initials B.P.
By the way,
have you ever done
any embroidery?
Embroidery?
You know -- needlework.
That sort of thing.
No.
And what of the perfect crime?
It is an illusion, Countess.
Maybe.
But let me tell you
something I heard.
It was a robbery
like the one at Mr. Hardman's,
but this time, it was diamonds.
Please go on.
Twelve people sat down
to dinner.
The safe was in the next room.
The hostess herself had checked
that the diamonds were in place
before the meal had begun.
And after?
The safe was open
and empty.
And there were no clues?
None.
It is strange
that you should choose
to relate this to me, Countess.
I also have read of it.
Yes?
Oh, yes.
The Atterton diamonds.
And it is true that the police,
they were confounded,
but that is because they look
with the eyes that is too...
English.
I don't understand.
Well, they see the dukes
and the duchesses,
the lords and the ladies,
but they fail to ask themselves
the one simple question.
Which is?
What person was at that dinner
who was also at the soiree
of M. Hardman
and on two other occasions
when some jewels were stolen?
So you are saying
the police cannot solve it
because they are too English?
Or because the culprit,
he is not English enough.
Thank you for
a really lovely day.
Countess.
Will I see you tomorrow?
For a déjeuner?
Oui.
The Carlton Hotel.
Bernard Parker must have been
in love with Lady Runcorn.
He gave her the embroidery,
but lied about it to us.
I think Johnstone
was lying, as well.
I'm sure it's him.
I say, Poirot.
Learning Russian?
I wonder why.
It has been an invaluable aid,
mon ami.
Yes, I couldn't get past
the alphabet, myself.
No, it is indeed complicated.
Yes, like this case.
The stolen jewels?
We've been investigating,
Mr. Poirot.
You're not the only private
detective in London, you know.
This is true, mon ami.
Eh bien, tell me all
that you have discovered.
So we think Bernard Parker
is blackmailing Lady Runcorn.
We've discovered
she has huge debts,
and she's recently sent
four paintings to auction.
She must have sold them
to pay him off.
So you say Lady Runcorn
requires money?
Yes.
So is it not more likely
that Lady Runcorn
would meet with
M. Bernard Parker
to discuss the selling
of her jewels?
That is his occupation,
is it not?
Ah, but what about
the embroidery?
He signed it "B.P."
But then I wonder
what Lady Runcorn was called
before she became Lady Runcorn.
Oh.
Oh, I hadn't thought of that.
If you are to be Hercule Poirot,
you must think of everything.
Lady Runcorn.
Born Beatrice Palmerston.
B.P.
He's right.
So, all right, then, Poirot.
What do you think?
I think, Hastings, you must ask
yourself one question.
Yes?
The tramp.
What was he doing there?
And the answer?
You will find only by returning
to the home
of M. Marcus Hardman.
I suggest that you go tomorrow.
Well, what about you?
This case does not
interest Poirot.
I have no enthusiasm for it.
And it is as you yourself say,
Hastings.
There are other
private detectives.
Yes, I'm sure.
What about poor old Japp?
Hmm.
No, sir, nothing as yet, sir.
But I am following up
a few leads.
Uh, well, no, sir, they haven't
actually led anywhere yet.
Well, if you could just give me
a little bit more time --
48 hours?
Well, I was hoping for a little
bit more time than that, sir.
I can assure you, sir,
your wife is perfectly safe.
If you'd like to put her on,
I can assure her myself, sir.
No, sir, I didn't mean that,
sir.
Right, sir.
Yes, sir.
I am working on it, sir.
I'll do that, sir.
Thank you.
Good evening.
Please allow me
to introduce myself.
Poirot?
Not the Hercule Poirot?
The very same.
Please, sit down, sir.
No, thank you.
What can we do for you?
I have a friend who requires
my immediate help.
But I cannot help,
and so I turn to you.
You mean you want us to sort of
deputize for you?
Oui, c'est ça.
You must act on my behalf.
It must be something important
for you to ask for our help,
M. Poirot.
It is a matter of the utmost
importance, monsieur.
There is a reputation --
No, there is a life
that is at stake.
But Hercule Poirot
is not involved.
The tramp.
What was the tramp doing here?
I can't see how wandering around
the grounds
is going to give us the answer.
Let's be methodical,
Captain Hastings.
Mr. Poirot must have a reason
for sending us here.
Four people went
into that house.
You'd have thought one of them
must have done it.
How about Lady Runcorn?
If her name was
Beatrice Palmerston once,
the cigarette case
could have belonged to her.
B.P.
Maybe she was working
with Bernard Parker.
They were in the house
at the same time.
What about that wretched tramp?
I just don't see
where he fits in.
Miss Lemon, look!
Over there.
It's him.
Wait here.
Hey, you!
Stop!
Captain Hastings!
He's got a gun!
Are you all right?
I think so.
Listen.
Well, that's the first tramp
I've seen
behind the wheel of an MG.
Ow!
It's iodine, Captain Hastings.
I said it'd sting.
It is me who suffers, my friend,
to think that I sent you.
Oh, it's not your fault, Poirot.
But, yes, Hastings.
It was me who sent you
to the house,
and but for your speed
and agility --
He fired four times, Mr. Poirot!
I know, Miss Lemon.
Did you know the tramp
would come back?
No, but I am an imbecile.
I see only half of the picture.
I don't even see that.
Miss Lemon, would you be so good
as to telephone
the Chief Inspector Japp?
Ask him to meet us at the home
of Marcus Hardman.
What about your lunch
with the countess?
Ah! Well...
we will meet after lunch.
At 3:00.
Where are you taking her?
It is the countess who takes me.
You astonish me, madame.
I am lost in admiration.
It's just a picnic.
We used to have such picnics.
Suppose he --
Poirot and the countess...
He wouldn't.
Would he?
I don't know.
I've never seen him
like this before.
And now a toast.
I shall propose one, if I may.
To crime.
That is a strange toast,
coming from a detective.
And yet it is my raison d'être.
My life is ruled by it.
And it is crime
that has brought us together.
Then, to crime.
He couldn't.
He just couldn't.
You'd be out of a situation.
And what about you?
Oh, I could travel.
I've always had a dream about
South America, you know.
Farming.
You'd miss him, though,
wouldn't you?
Of course I would.
What about you?
I don't want to talk about it.
And now, I think --
Yes.
I have an investigation
with the Chief Inspector Japp.
And it must be resolved.
Is there anything I can do?
This time I fear
the culprit may escape,
or this time,
the culprit may never be named.
That depends entirely upon you.
Me?
I think so.
Could this help?
Only four people came into
the house during the concert.
The countess, M. Johnstone,
Lady Runcorn,
and M. Bernard Parker.
The thorough investigation
of my colleagues
eliminated M. Johnstone
and Lady Runcorn.
M. Johnstone,
because he's a very wealthy man.
And Lady Runcorn?
Lady Runcorn because
she came to the house
in order to meet
with M. Bernard Parker.
Is that not so, M. Hardman?
Yes.
But no one must know.
My whole business --
it thrives on nobody knowing.
D'accord.
And finally,
there is the countess,
who entered the house
in order to get her coat.
Her coat?
I thought it was a warm evening.
Yes, it was, Chief Inspector.
But I had been outside
for more than an hour.
Well, yes, but --
And forgive me,
but if that Japanese contralto
had sung one more high note,
my head would have shattered.
And while you were
inside, Countess,
you caught sight of a figure,
non?
And you disturbed him,
n'est-ce pas?
Yes, but I only glimpsed him.
Going where?
From this room to the window.
Ah, yes.
The window
with a climbing plant.
That brings us to the tramp
and one very important
question --
why did he come back?
Yes, and how could he afford
an MG, for that matter?
The tramp who was no tramp
used the climbing plant
in order to enter the house.
Now, for him,
the window was no obstacle.
The safe, also,
he opened with ease.
So what about the clues?
The glove belonged
to M. Bernard Parker.
It was put there
to incriminate him.
The case belonged
to Lady Runcorn --
or Beatrice Palmerston,
as once she was called.
But always, I think,
she will deny it.
Why?
Because she brought it here
in order to sell it.
She'll never admit that.
She's too proud.
That is quite true, Miss Lemon.
So the tramp took the jewels?
What did he do then?
He returned to the window,
where he was disturbed
by the countess.
He slipped, and he fell.
And the necklace?
The necklace, he dropped,
which is why
he had to come back.
Wait a minute.
I've got it.
Voilà.
Green against green.
My necklace.
What about the tramp?
I'd still like to collar him,
you know, Poirot.
Oui, d'accord, but I fear
it is too late.
What's the matter?
Just something she said.
Who?
The countess.
She said the singer
was Japanese.
It was the pianist
who was Japanese.
What of it?
Well, if she really had been
in the garden for an hour,
surely she would have known.
Good night.
Miss Lemon, I thought
you had already gone.
No, I had some letters
to finish.
You're working late, Mr. Poirot?
Yes, I have from
the Chief Inspector Japp
the reports
of the jewelry thefts.
This work, Miss Lemon --
sometimes it is not
so straightforward.
You do work so hard,
Mr. Poirot.
Sometimes I think,
really, you ought --
Yes, Miss Lemon?
Nothing, Mr. Poirot.
Good night, Miss Lemon.
Good night.
Ten minutes until your train.
Yes.
And then your ship to America.
Thank you.
Madame, you are
the most remarkable,
the most unique woman
that I have ever met.
But also --
Opposites.
C'est ça.
You must continue your work,
and I must continue mine.
But not in the same country.
Countess, please allow me
to introduce
two colleagues of mine --
Messieurs Redfern and Blake.
Good evening, ma'am.
They are, like myself,
private detectives.
Do you really think
I need an escort?
No, no, no, no.
They are for your protection.
During your short visit
in England,
there have been four
very clever robberies.
I would not wish you to be
involved in a fifth.
Of course.
Are they armed?
I believe that M. Redfern
does carry a gun.
Yes, loaded with blanks,
of course.
Ah, yes.
M. Redfern played the tramp
more convincingly
than I had expected.
But pauvre Hastings.
I am afraid
that it was necessary
to lead him off the scent.
But I forget.
I have something for you.
A parting present?
A souvenir.
The cigarette case?
The double clue.
It's of no use to me.
It's inscribed "B.P."
Yes.
And yet,
in the Russian alphabet,
a "B" is a "V,"
and a "P" is an "R," is it not?
Vera Rossakoff?
You've been studying.
You will keep it, I hope?
Something to remember me by.
Oh.
I won't forget you.
Hercule.
Nor I you,
Countess.
Au revoir.