You're not serious.
You can't be.
It was a joke, that's all.
I was joking.
We are English, for God's sake.
My God.
Fertig?
Ready?
Los!
I never knew you were so keen
on opera, Poirot.
Generally, mon ami, I am not,
but the Rigoletto.
The father who is jealous.
His daughter, she is dishonored,
so he plans the murder parfait,
but he has failed to understand
the psychology,
and the result, catastrophe.
That is what interests me.
Well, it does have a couple
of good tunes, I suppose.
M. Poirot.
M. Poirot, I hope you'll
forgive me intruding like this,
but when I saw you,
I couldn't believe it.
It is Lady Chatterton,
is it not?
You remember me!
Oh, but then,
of course, you would.
I was there when you solved
the Chalfont Diamonds case.
I was one of the suspects.
It was so thrilling,
and I have to say,
M. Poirot,
you were magnificent.
Yes.
I've never forgotten
seeing you at work.
That's what made me wonder...
There is something troubling
you, Lady Chatterton?
Yes, there is.
Not me, you understand.
My friend, Mrs. Clayton.
I'm sure she's in danger,
M. Poirot.
Is that Mr. Clayton with her?
Oh, no, no, just a friend.
That's Major Rich.
Could you call on me tomorrow?
I'm sure
you're a busy man, but...
Lady Chatterton,
I will call on you
at 11:00 in the morning.
Thank you, M. Poirot.
Marguerite Clayton is one
of my dearest friends.
As you saw,
she's a very beautiful woman,
notoriously so.
It is said that 10 years ago,
two of her admirers actually
fought a duel over her.
-In England?
-Yes.
Nobody understood why
she chose Edward Clayton.
She could have married anybody.
He has a violent temper,
M. Poirot.
Marguerite lives
in constant fear of him,
and recently, his behavior
has become very strange.
So quiet, so detached,
as if he were
planning something.
M. Poirot,
I think Edward Clayton
is going to murder his wife.
Yes, sir?
Good morning.
I wonder if you can help me.
There's something
I'm looking for,
but I don't quite know
how to describe it.
It's a type of knife.
Edward?
You're early.
Yes. I won't be able to come
to Major Rich's this evening,
Marguerite.
Why can't you come tonight?
I have to go to Edinburgh.
There have been
some complications
in the Gordon case.
Can't your clerk sort it out?
No, it needs
my personal attention,
but I'm sure you'll enjoy
yourselves without me.
Would you prefer it
if I didn't go?
No, I'd prefer it if you went.
I don't see why you should
sit in by yourself.
Have you told Major Rich?
No, I'll look in this afternoon.
I'm at the club until 4:00,
but I can call in
on my way to the station.
Well, if that's
what you want, Edward.
Yes, that's what I want.
Have a lovely time.
Well, it's none of
my business what you do.
You've told her
you're going to Scotland?
I just don't know if I can
go through with this, Curtiss.
You want to know, don't you?
Do I?
These last six months,
you've looked
as if you're wasting away.
I know.
I keep stepping back and saying,
"This is madness."
Well?
I will do it.
I'll do it.
That's four
and ninepence, gov.
Thank you.
Good afternoon, Burgoyne.
Good afternoon, sir.
Is Major Rich in?
I'm sorry, sir.
Major Rich has been out
since early this morning.
Did he say what time
he'd be back?
No, sir.
I don't think
he'll be long, though.
All right, I'll wait.
If he doesn't come back
in a few minutes,
I'll leave a note for him.
Certainly, sir.
May I fetch you a pen?
No, it's all right.
I have one.
Thank you.
You can just get on
with your duties, Burgoyne.
I'll leave a note for him
in the sitting room.
Very good, sir.
I'd like a word with you,
Major Rich.
Mrs. Clayton...
is a very old and dear friend
of mine, Major.
There's been a lot of talk
about you and her.
Too much talk, Rich.
Now, look, Curtiss,
I don't know what any of this
has to do with you.
As much or as little
as I choose.
Mrs. Clayton finds your
attentions offensive, sir.
Now, just you listen to me...
No, no, no. Your attentions
are unwelcome, Major.
Just get that into your head,
will you?
If they continue,
I should be obliged to put
an end to them myself.
You understand?
Good afternoon, sir.
Oh, hello, Burgoyne.
I believe Mr. Clayton
is waiting for you
in the sitting room, sir.
Clayton?
Yes, sir.
Hmm.
No, there's no one here.
Said he would wait for a few
minutes and then leave a note,
but I didn't hear him go, sir.
How much longer
is Miss Lemon on holiday?
I can't make head or tail
of her filing system.
She is in Frinton for
one more week, mon ami.
What is it
that you are looking for?
I thought we might
have something
on this Edward Clayton.
You're looking very smart.
Thank you, mon ami.
I'm going to a party
with Lady Chatterton.
I'm going to meet
the sinister Edward Clayton.
I suppose you think
he'll take one look at you
and change his mind
about murdering his wife.
All things are possible.
Come on, Poirot, admit it.
You're only going so you can be
fussed over by Lady Chatterton.
You took this case on
simply because of the way
she buttered you up.
You think it is wrong,
Hastings,
to enjoy the compliments,
or the buttering, as you say?
No, but, uh,
do you have to show it
quite so much?
It's not English.
Perhaps it is Belgian.
Hastings, why should
I be the hypocrite,
to blush when I am praised
and to say,
like you, "It is nothing."
I have the order, the mettle,
and the psychology.
There, I admit it.
I am the best.
I am Hercule Poirot,
and now I think
it is time for me to go.
A perfect gentleman
must not keep waiting a lady.
There is Mme. Clayton.
Yes.
I can't see her husband, though.
She is speaking
with her friend,
Major Rich, yes?
Caroline,
so glad you could come.
John.
This is Hercule Poirot,
a friend of mine.
Major Rich.
Hercule Poirot.
I know that name.
Ah.
You're the writer.
No.
Where's Edward?
He, uh, couldn't make it,
I'm afraid.
Oh.
Are you over here
on holiday, Mr. Poirot?
No.
I live here.
Ah. Well, have a drink.
It's all very informal.
Thank you.
Lady Chatterton.
-Merci.
I'm so sorry, M. Poirot.
Edward Clayton's not here.
Eh bien,
I can relax and enjoy myself.
Indeed.
...to see you here,
Colonel Curtiss.
So, do you wish to withdraw
the invitation?
No.
Mary used to love dancing.
John lost his wife
a few months ago.
My condolences, Major Rich.
Edward hates this modern music.
It's just as well he's not here.
Your husband,
he is unwell, madame?
No.
He has business in Scotland.
Ah, and does he
abandon you very often,
your husband?
I can assure you that, normally,
Mr. Clayton keeps
a firm grip on Mrs. Clayton.
A stranglehold, you mean.
Put on something
with a bit of a fizz.
"These Foolish Things"?
No!
"Nobody's Sweetheart"?
Yes, that will do.
Music for second-rate people
provided by
the inferior races, what?
That is not a very pleasant
thing to say, monsieur.
You're not dancing,
M. Poirot.
Oh, no, no, no, Lady Chatterton.
This music is for
the young people,
with the limbs that are supple.
I'm sure
you're a wonderful dancer.
No, no, no, no, truly.
But tell me, madame,
who is that unpleasant man over
there with the walking stick?
Unpleasant?
Colonel Curtiss?
He's an old friend
of Marguerite's.
Why do you say "unpleasant"?
Now, come along, M. Poirot.
I insist.
Oh!
Charleston.
This, I cannot drink.
There must be no more than three
spoons of sugar in my tisane.
That is the way
Miss Lemon prepares it.
I put three spoons in.
Then Miss Lemon must use
a spoon that is smaller.
I'll get it.
Chief Inspector.
Hastings.
Morning, Poirot.
Ah, Chief Inspector Japp,
bonjour.
You're on a matter
of importance, yes?
For you are up with the bird.
Lark.
Cup of tea, Chief Inspector?
No, thank you.
Please be seated,
Chief Inspector.
You have come for my help,
I think.
Well, yes, you could say that.
Thing is, you see,
I've come to interview you.
Interview?
As a witness.
Witness to what?
You were at the Belgravia home
of Major John Rich last night?
Yes.
This morning,
I arrested Major Rich
for the murder
of Edward Clayton.
Mon Dieu.
You're saying
that I am a witness?
Did you, by any chance,
remark on an elaborate
wooden chest
in the room where you were,
a Spanish chest,
I believe it's called?
No, I don't think...
The manservant Burgoyne
discovered the body
inside this chest
when he was cleaning the room.
Clayton's blood had seeped
into the carpet.
He'd been stabbed
through the eye,
straight into the brain.
You're telling me that
the body was there while --
While the rest of you listened
to music and drank cocktails
and danced or whatever it is
you got up to, yes.
It's pretty macabre,
isn't it?
It's revolting.
Chief Inspector,
you are convinced
that the killer is Major Rich?
Rich was in love
with Marguerite Clayton.
That was the motive,
and he had the opportunity.
Clayton called round to see him
a few hours before
the first guests arrived.
You think that Major Rich,
he came home,
he killed Edward Clayton,
put the body in the chest,
and then, later, he entertained
his guests in the same room?
That's about the size of it.
No.
No, Chief Inspector.
And again, I say no.
It is not possible
that Major Rich
killed Edward Clayton.
I swear to heaven, Mr. Poirot,
I never saw him.
Have you any idea
why Edward Clayton
should have wished to see you?
None at all.
According to Marguerite --
Mrs. Clayton --
he was on his way to Scotland.
Had you ever discussed
Mme. Clayton with her husband?
And why should I do that,
Mr. Poirot?
Forgive me, Major Rich, but...
how long ago is it
since your wife died?
I know what you're insinuating
Mr. Poirot,
but there was never anything
improper between us.
No.
Very good, sir.
Colonel Curtiss
will see you now, sir.
-Smithy!
-Sir.
Take these gentlemen through
to the strangers' room.
Yes, sir.
It's this way, gentlemen.
Thank you.
That's the, uh, gymnasium
through there.
There is a gymnasium here?
Oh, yes.
There's weights, fencing,
parallel bars.
It's very popular
with the members.
Um, so you thinking
of joining, then?
-No.
-Oh, right.
Um, we'll go this way.
And, uh, there's no talking.
Excuse me, Colonel Curtiss.
Your guests.
Thank you, Smithy.
-Colonel Curtiss.
-How do you do?
I'd like to introduce my
associate, Captain Hastings.
How do you do?
Please, sit down.
Thank you.
Well, I'm sure
you don't need to tell me
why you're here, Mr. Poirot.
It's a dreadful business.
Dreadful.
-Then you have heard?
-Yes.
Your chappie at Scotland Yard
seemed to find it amusing
that you were there last night.
And you?
I think it's a godsend.
I mean, you're a detective.
I am the detective,
Colonel Curtiss.
Then I don't need to tell you
that Major Rich, in my opinion,
could never...
May I ask you, Colonel Curtiss,
how did you come to know
Edward Clayton?
I knew Mrs. Clayton
before they married.
Was Mr. Clayton
a friend of yours?
Of course.
He was Marguerite's husband.
I understand that Edward Clayton
came to visit you
here at the club yesterday.
That's right.
What passed between you?
Oh, not much.
Had a drink together.
Told me he was going
to Scotland,
but that he'd look in at Rich's
on his way to the station.
Did he say why?
No.
To apologize for missing
the party, I imagine.
Had he ever hinted
at any impropriety
between Major Rich
and Marguerite Clayton?
Certainly not.
My apologies.
Colonel Curtiss,
I try only to establish
the facts.
Well, he wasn't much help,
was he?
Did you remark upon
his scar, Hastings?
Yes. You probably need one
to be a member here.
Marguerite,
you shouldn't have come.
I had to see you.
I don't know what to do, John.
There's nothing you can do.
Can't you leave us alone,
Officer?
The police questioned me.
Margo...
I didn't kill him.
There's a private detective,
too, asking questions.
Just tell them the truth.
How can I?
I know it seems hard, Margo,
but if you just
tell the truth...
I'm sorry.
I can't stay here.
I'm sorry, John.
Marguerite.
I-I shouldn't have come here.
I left Mr. Clayton here
outside the sitting room door.
That must have been
just after 6:00.
I went to press
Major Rich's evening suit.
But Mr. Clayton didn't leave,
you say?
I think I would have heard him
if he'd gone.
Bien.
Tell me, M. Burgoyne,
when your master returned,
did you actually see him enter
at the door?
I heard the door close, sir.
But you did not see him enter?
No, sir.
Thank you.
If you please,
we will now go inside.
You think Major Rich
was waiting for Clayton?
It is possible, Hastings.
He kills Edward Clayton,
he puts the body inside
the chest, he comes out,
he shuts the door to establish
that he has just arrived.
Let us look
at this Spanish chest.
Alors.
It is not the same.
Ah, the carpet
has been taken up, sir.
You see, Hastings, this chest,
it is clearly visible
from the door, yes?
But...
Yes.
The screen conceals most of it
from the rest of the room.
If you please, Hastings.
What do you make of this,
Hastings?
Woodworm?
Come, Hastings.
There is nothing more
for us here.
Well, Major Rich certainly had
the opportunity to kill Clayton,
and as for motive, well...
Go on, mon ami.
Well, Mrs. Clayton.
It doesn't look too good
for him, does it?
You think not, Hastings?
I wonder what the beautiful
Mme. Clayton
has to say about all this.
Romaine Gardens, if you please.
Oh, quick, gentlemen,
please, please help me.
Something terrible
has happened.
She's locked herself
in there, sir.
I can't get no answer
when I knock.
Quick, mademoiselle,
telephone for the doctor.
I've washed out her stomach.
She ought to rest.
We shall take one
or two minutes only, Doctor.
You do understand the urgency
of the situation?
Yes. No more than
five minutes, though.
Oui, d'accord.
Merci beaucoup.
It's my fault.
It was all my fault.
Major Rich and I,
we'd always been friends,
but that was all.
Until his wife died.
Oh.
It was all my fault,
Mr. Poirot.
What did you do?
I prayed
for my husband's death.
I wanted Edward to die.
Major Rich knew my feelings.
We talked about it.
But only...
he must have misunderstood me.
He must have thought I was
asking him to kill my husband.
That's why he did it.
Oh, God.
This is difficult, Hastings.
Very difficult.
Le tarte aux fraises,
s'il vous plaît.
Just a cup of coffee
for me, please.
Merci.
To commit a crime, yes,
but then to invite 20 people
into the same room?
Major Rich has stabbed
Edward Clayton.
He has put the body into
the Spanish chest minutes before
a party is due to start.
Thank you.
But what about the valet,
Hastings, what of him?
He would be certain to discover
the body in the morning.
Now, Major Rich
would have known that.
So why did not the major
dispose of the body
during the night?
Hastings,
I must return to
the Scotland Yard
and the Chief Inspector Japp.
-Oh, I'll come with you.
-No, no, no, no.
You will take yourself
to the military club.
There is there,
I think, a gymnasium.
What's a gymnasium
got to do with it?
That is precisely what
you will find out for me.
Detecting's
not what it was, you know.
They expect you to be
a blooming secretary.
How do you make
this thing go backwards?
How do you mean?
I want to go back
and type over something.
There must be some sort of
reverse gear.
It isn't that one, is it?
See who that is.
Bonjour, Sergeant.
Mr. Poirot, sir.
Ah, come in, Poirot.
All right.
Take a seat.
I'll be with you --
Oh, damn and blast it!
All this paperwork.
You any good with one of these?
No, and my own Miss Lemon
is, alas...
-Not ill, is she?
-Worse.
She is at Frinton.
Chief Inspector,
I need to see the contents of
the pockets of Edward Clayton
at the time that he was taken
from the chest.
It's very popular with
the members, the gymnasium.
And that's where it happened?
That's what I was told.
Before my time, though.
But there was a duel?
Yeah, at 6:00 in the morning.
I don't know who they were,
so you needn't bother to ask.
Why did they fight?
Why do you think -- it was over
some woman, wasn't it?
Marguerite Clayton.
I don't know who it was.
Now, about my 10 bob.
Mm.
These two men...
Was one of them having an affair
with Marguerite Clayton?
Now, that was
the barmy thing about it.
It was all just a joke.
One of the officers made
a joke about the lady,
so the other one called him out.
That's all it was, a joke.
Wasn't any sort of joke, though,
go and get yourself
sliced up like salami.
Yes, we wondered about that.
But I expected it.
Voilà!
Yes.
It's for you.
Hastings.
Hello?
Yes, Hastings?
Good.
But he did not tell you
the people involved?
Excellent, Hastings.
Excellent.
Well?
Chief Inspector Japp,
I must ask you to trust me
as you have never
trusted me before.
Here we go.
Yes, but we have never before
faced a crime that is perfect,
committed with such coldness.
It is remarkable, unique.
I don't know
why I bother sometimes.
I may as well stay at home
and do my garden.
Who do you want me
to arrest now?
Mrs. Clayton, this way!
Is it true you're still
investigating?
Is she under arrest, Inspector?
M. Poirot, how long have you
been involved in the case?
Did you arrange to have
Mrs. Clayton arrested?
I have nothing to say.
All right, Rich,
pack your kit.
You're going out.
Hello?
You've got it wrong,
Mr. Poirot.
I know who killed
Edward Clayton.
You know who --
Meet me at the military club
in the gymnasium.
Who is this, please?
I'll show you.
Hello?
Colonel Curtiss.
You've got it wrong,
you bloody little frog!
You've arrested
Marguerite Clayton.
You've degraded her,
soiled her!
But she had nothing
to do with it.
Two things, Colonel Curtiss.
Firstly, I am not
a bloody little frog.
I am a bloody little Belgian.
Secondly, I know quite well
that Marguerite Clayton
is innocent.
Go on.
Edward Clayton believed his wife
to be unfaithful.
There was talk,
but he was not certain,
so he came to you, his friend,
and you suggested
a scheme fantastique.
Will you listen to me?
Will you do as I say?
I just don't know if I can
go through with it, Curtiss.
M. Clayton was obsessed
with the possibility
that his wife
had been unfaithful,
and so you fueled his jealousy
for your own ends.
First, you tell him he must play
the old, old trick
of pretending to go away.
A business trip to Scotland
will do very nicely.
Then he gains admission
to the house of Major Rich
under the pretext
of leaving a note.
Then, following your scheme,
Edward Clayton conceals himself
inside the Spanish chest.
Now he can hear for himself
what takes place.
Perhaps he will hear Major Rich
make love to his wife,
but at least the torment
will be over.
He will know.
But there is one further
consideration.
To breathe inside the box,
he needs the air,
and so, with the instrument
he has brought,
he makes a hole through which
he can not only breathe,
but, most important of all,
through which he can observe.
But the poor, deluded Clayton.
He did not know that you also
were in love with Marguerite,
that you had always loved her,
fought even a duel for her.
Fertig?
Ready?
We are English, for God's sake!
Who told you that?
I was joking.
Your scar.
Aah!
Your first scheme
had been merely
to get rid of Edward Clayton,
but even with her husband
out of the way,
you began to fear
that she might eventually
turn to a younger man.
Major Rich.
This last scheme of yours
would encompass them both.
With one stroke,
Edward Clayton is dead,
and Major Rich will hang
for the murder.
Nobody knows I'm here.
When the police
find you tomorrow,
they'll know they were wrong
to release Rich.
You still wish to fight
for Marguerite Clayton
after all these years?
But not with me, I think.
Will you fight for her,
Colonel?
Damn you!
Los!
Aah!
I'm forever in your debt,
Mr. Poirot.
Eh bien, madame,
it was nothing.
My husband was not
a likeable man, but...
to be murdered in cold blood.
I don't see why you had
Mrs. Clayton arrested.
Major Rich, it was necessary
to smoke out
the Colonel Curtiss,
you understand?
And to make a public spectacle
of Mme. Clayton.
It was the only way.
You were wonderful.
Well, as they say, madame...
it was nothing.
I was... lucky,
that is all.
We'll always be grateful
to you, Mr. Poirot.
Thank you.
Always.
Madame.
-Goodbye.
Nothing?
Lucky?
I am learning, Hastings.
It is more English, yes,
the humbleness?
Well, I am learning.
I shall be
the most humble person
in the world.
No one shall match
Hercule Poirot
for his "humbility."