- I KINDA WANNA
GET MY OWN PLACE WITH JENNI.
- REALLY?
- YEAH.
- NICOLE'S A HANDFUL.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
IT'S GONNA BE CRAZY.
- IS THIS IT?
- IS THIS A GARAGE?
- SO WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK
OF THE OPEN FEELING THOUGH?
- I LOVE THIS PLACE.
- SO BEFORE WE GET
ALL SERIOUS AND SIGN THE LEASE,
I REALLY NEED
TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
SO JIONNI PROPOSED.
AND I'M PREGNANT.
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT, I LOVE IT *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
[pop music playing]
* *
- UM--
SO HE PRETTY MUCH
ASKED ME TO GET MARRIED
BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT.
LIKE, THREE MONTHS.
- WHAT DO I SAY?
- I'M PREGNANT.
AND ENGAGED.
WILL YOU BE THE GODMOTHER?
- OH, MY GOD!
REALLY?
- YEAH.
- NO. AWW.
I'M SHAKING.
I CAN'T PROCESS WHAT NICOLE
IS TELLING ME RIGHT NOW.
I WANNA BE SO HAPPY FOR HER,
BUT AT THE SAME TIME,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
I'M GETTING MYSELF INTO.
- SO DO YOU WANNA
GET THIS PLACE?
[chuckles]
- COME WITH ME.
- I'M DEFINITELY NERVOUS THAT
JENNI'S NOT GONNA WANNA
LIVE WITH ME.
I REALLY WANNA DO THIS,
BECAUSE
IT'S THE ONLY TIME
I CAN DO IT--
LIKE, LITERALLY.
- JESUS [bleep].
THIS IS MORE OF A DECISION
FOR YOU THAN ME.
- YOU KNOW MY DECISION.
YES, I LOVE THIS PLACE.
LET'S GET IT.
- PREGNANT AND ENGAGED NICOLE
SEEMS LIKE SHE'S
ALL ABOUT IT.
BUT I'M TRYING TO HOLD ON
TO MY TWENTIES.
AM I GONNA TURN
INTO HER MOM
THAT BRINGS HER
TO HER DOCTORS
AND HOLDS HER HAIR WHILE
SHE'S THROWING UP?
LIKE, I DON'T KNOW
HOW PREGNANT CHICKS ACT.
- THIS IS GONNA BE
REALLY FUN.
SO DON'T THINK IT'S NOT
GOING TO BE.
- I TRUST YOU.
I'M SURE YOU CAN
MAKE ANYTHING FUN.
I'M SURE IF WE WERE
IN A JAIL CELL--
- IT WOULD BE A BLAST,
EVEN IF I HAD
TWO KIDS ON MY ARM.
- SO YOU WANNA DO THIS?
- YES.
[burps]
- SO WHAT DID YOU GUYS--
WHAT'S THE CONCLUSION?
- WE'RE GONNA TAKE IT!
- NICE.
- WHOO!
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- SO EXCITED.
- CHEERS.
IT'S NOT CHAMPAGNE,
BUT IT'LL DO.
- SO ALL YOU GUYS NEED
TO DO NOW IS JUST INITIAL--
- ALL THREE?
- ALL THREE.
- I MEAN, HONESTLY,
I DON'T EVEN READ
THE FRICKIN' PAPERS,
WHICH IS REALLY BAD.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
both: THANK YOU.
- GOOD LUCK WITH EVERYTHING.
- YOU KNOW, I JUST WANT
THIS PLACE.
I JUST WANNA MOVE IN WITH JENNI
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
- DON'T FORGET THE LEASE.
- OH, YEAH.
- I DON'T WANT IT.
- I HAVE TO SHOW
MY DAD THIS,
'CAUSE I WASN'T
SUPPOSED TO SIGN IT.
AND I KNOW MY DAD'S GONNA
KILL ME,
BECAUSE I'M NOT EVEN
CALLING HIM TO SAY
I'M SIGNING THE LEASE.
BUT, YOU KNOW, IT'S A NEW STEP
IN MY NEW LIFE.
- SEE YA TOMORROW?
- YEAH.
- AAH!
[bleep]
OKAY, I'M GOOD.
[techno music]
- * OH, MY GOD *
* *
- SO WE LOOKED AT HOUSES.
FOUND THIS ONE
THAT WE REALLY LIKED...
AND WE SIGNED PAPERS
AND WE'RE MOVING IN TOMORROW.
- WHAT?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
YOU SIGNED THE PAPERS?
- WE'RE MOVING IN TOMORROW.
- I THOUGHT WHEN WE LEFT YOU
WERE NOT GONNA SIGN ANYTHING.
WE WERE GONNA WORK IT OUT.
OH, THAT'S TERRIFIC.
- OKAY, SO--
HOW LONG DID YOU
SIGN THE LEASE FOR?
- [sighs] OH, BOY.
- IT DOESN'T MATTER.
- WHAT KINDA HEAT
IS IN IT?
OIL? GAS?
- WE DIDN'T ASK.
- YOU DIDN'T ASK?
- ELECTRIC?
- I DON'T KNOW.
WE JUST SAID,
"WE'LL TAKE IT."
- [chuckles]
- WELL--
- THAT'S IT.
- I REALLY WISH
YOU WOULD'VE CALLED ME.
- MY DAD'S MAKING
ALL THESE FACES.
AND I'M LIKE,
"DAD, IT'S FINE.
"LIKE, STOP BEING
SO INVESTIGATOR.
EVERYTHING'S GONNA
BE FINE."
IT'S TIME TO GROW UP.
- UH, YEAH.
- YOU KNOW,
I REALLY DON'T CARE.
LIKE, NO OFFENSE, DAD,
BUT I'M DOING THIS
WHETHER YOU LIKE IT
OR NOT.
GOOD NIGHT.
DON'T WAKE ME UP.
- [laughs]
- SHE IS JUST, LIKE--
I DON'T--
I DON'T FRICKIN' BELIEVE THIS.
[rock music]
* *
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- WE FOUND A REALLY
NICE PLACE.
- YOU FOUND ONE.
WHERE IS IT?
JERSEY CITY STILL?
- JERSEY CITY.
AND THEN, UM--
SOMEBODY'S KNOCKED UP.
- WHAT?
- NICOLE HAD TO TELL ME
THAT SHE'S PREGNANT.
- GET THE [bleep]
OUT OF HERE.
- I ALMOST THREW UP
ON MYSELF.
AND JIONNI PROPOSED
TO HER LAST MONTH.
- GET THE [bleep]
OUT OF HERE, SERIOUSLY.
- I WANNA HAVE AN EXPERIENCE
WITH HER BEFORE
SHE HITS HER THIRD TRIMESTER.
- SHE'S PREGNANT.
- YES.
- HOW ARE YOU GONNA
HAVE ANY FUN?
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA TAKE
[bleep] LAMAZE CLASS WITH HER?
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
JENNI SPRINGS THIS ON ME,
AND TELLS ME NICOLE
IS NOW PREGNANT.
AND SHE'S STILL GOING THROUGH
WITH THIS MOVE.
AM I IN THE [bleep]
TWILIGHT ZONE?
THAT MAKES NO SENSE.
IF NICOLE IS DRIVING
YOU BONKERS
AND YOU CAN'T TAKE IT,
DON'T CALL ME CRYING.
YOU MADE THE CHOICE.
- DON'T MAKE ME
TWIST YOUR NIPPLE.
- DON'T TOUCH MY TITTIES.
- AS ROGER'S TALKING,
THE REALITY'S SETTING IN.
LIKE, I'M LEGIT MOVING IN
WITH A CHICK THAT'S
PREGNANT AND ENGAGED.
IS THAT WHAT I WANT?
- WHY DOES SHE DO THAT TO US?
THAT'S OKAY.
YOU LEAVING ME TOO?
WHAT THE [bleep]?
DO I STINK?
JENNI, I'M PUTTING IN
AN OFFICIAL REQUEST
FOR JIONNI'S BACHELOR PARTY.
- NO.
I DON'T WANT NO DIRTY SKANK
GRINDING ON HIM.
- WHY ARE YOU COOL
WITH IT THEN?
- HE WOULD LEAVE ME
IF I WAS LIKE THAT.
- [laughing]
- YO.
- AAH!
[giggles]
- WAKE UP.
- WHO IS IT?
- GOOD MORNING.
YOU TOLD JENNI?
- MM-HMM.
- IS SHE EXCITED?
- I THINK.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
YOU THINK?
HOW WAS HER REACTION?
- "YOU'RE LYING.
SHUT UP."
SHE GOT, LIKE, CONCERNED.
SHE THINKS WE'RE TOO YOUNG,
I FEEL.
- NO.
WE'LL SHOW HER WE'RE READY.
HOW'S MY LITTLE--
LET ME SEE.
I DON'T WANT ANYTHING TO HAPPEN.
- STOP TOUCHING!
- IT'S MY--
- WAIT TILL IT'S LARGE
AND IN CHARGE.
JIONNI THINKS IT'S OKAY
TO START
RUBBING MY STOMACH
AND POKING IT.
BUT AT THIS STAGE
IN THE PREGNANCY,
IT'S ONLY THREE MONTHS.
SO IT'S CREEPY.
- GET UP SLOW.
- YOU'RE SO ANNOYING.
- BABE.
- WHAT'S UP?
- YOUR CAR'S LEAKING
ANTIFREEZE OR SOMETHING.
SEE?
IT'S, LIKE, A PUDDLE
UNDER THERE.
IT'S A BRAND-NEW CAR.
- MY CAR IS LEAKING
SOMETHING.
LIKE, REALLY?
GO [bleep] FIGURE.
CAN I DRIVE IT?
- NO, YOU CAN'T DRIVE IT.
- IT'S, LIKE, A BAD OMEN.
IT'S LIKE GOD'S TELLING ME
I SHOULDN'T BE GOING TO
MOVE IN WITH HER.
SHOULD I EVEN BE MOVING
RIGHT NOW?
I FEEL LIKE THIS IS A SIGN.
DID I USE THAT WORD RIGHT?
- OMEN?
- YEAH.
- OKAY.
- JUST KNOW THAT YOU CAN'T
DRIVE IT LIKE THAT.
- I'M JUST THROWING STUFF
IN BAGS.
- JIONNI IS, LIKE, THE BEST
WHEN IT COMES
TO HELPING ME OUT
WITH THINGS.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
THE NICE BLOUSES
GO IN THAT.
OH, WAIT, W-W--
NO, NO, NO.
THANK GOD.
BECAUSE I WOULD FREAK OUT
IF I HAD TO DO ALL THIS MYSELF.
THAT'S NOT WHERE YOU PUT--
- OH, MY GOD.
IS THIS WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU GET MARRIED?
- THIS SUCKS.
- BABE, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT ELSE TO TELL YA.
I MEAN, IT'S GOTTA
GET FIXED.
YOU CAN'T DRIVE IT LIKE THAT,
SO--
- TOMORROW'S MY BIRTHDAY
AND I'M GONNA HAVE NO CAR.
- YOU HAVE NICOLE.
SHE HAS A CAR.
YOU WANT ME TO CALL 'EM?
- YEAH, I DIDN'T EVEN
INVITE THEM
TO MY BIRTHDAY PARTY YET,
SO YOU MIGHT AS WELL
INVITE 'EM FOR ME.
[phone ringing]
- ROGER'S CALLING.
ROGER.
- WHAT'S UP, BUDDY?
CONGRATULATIONS
IS IN ORDER
FOR YOUR AND NICOLE
I HEARD.
THAT'S AWESOME, MAN.
I'M HAPPY.
- WHAT'S THE OVER-UNDER ON HIM
BEING FIVE FOOT?
- WHAT'S THE OVER-UNDER ON BEING
FOUR FOOT IS MORE LIKE IT.
HE'S GONNA HAVE
GODZILLAARMS.
[laughter]
- IT'S NOT FUNNY.
MY BABY'S NOT GONNA HAVE
THESE KIND OF ARMS.
HE'S GONNA BE NORMAL.
- SHE'S 4'8".
I'M 4'10", SO--
[laughter]
- ALL RIGHT,
RELAX OVER THERE.
UM, LISTEN, I GOTTA
RUN SOMETHING BY YOU.
UH, JENNI'S BIRTHDAY
IS TOMORROW.
SHE WANTS TO GO OUT TO DINNER
WITH YOU AND NICOLE.
- UH, FOR YOU, ROG, WHY NOT?
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- I WILL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
- ALL RIGHT, LATER.
SO WE GOT IT FIGURED OUT.
THERE'S THE PLAN.
LET'S GET YOU OUT OF HERE.
I WAS JUST THINKING THOUGH,
THERE IS ANOTHER OPTION.
YOU COULD TAKE
MY WORK TRUCK.
YOU CAN'T DRIVE A STICK,
BUT I COULD TEACH YOU.
- ROGER'S LIKE, "LET ME TRY
AND TEACH YOU STICK.
YOU CAN DO THIS."
JESUS, MANUAL LOCKS
AND EVERYTHING?
- IT'S OLD-SCHOOL LIKE ME.
YOUR KEY GOES IN THERE.
- YEAH.
WHY WON'T IT START?
- 'CAUSE YOU HAVE TO PUSH
THE CLUTCH HERE
TO TAKE IT OUT OF GEAR.
TAKE THE EMERGENCY BRAKE OFF.
KEEP YOUR FOOT ON THE BRAKE.
PUSH THE CLUTCH IN.
PUT IT IN FIRST GEAR.
YOU KNOW WHERE
FIRST GEAR IS?
- THERE?
- LET OUT ON THE CLUTCH
REAL SLOWLY.
YOU'LL START TO FEEL IT--
EASY.
JESUS.
PUSH THE CLUTCH IN.
OKAY, THERE YOU GO.
THAT'S MUCH BETTER.
MUCH BETTER.
JESUS!
- I'M GOING.
[laughing]
OH, IT'S GOING. IT'S GOING.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS
RIGHT NOW?
- NO.
- WAS THAT A JOKE?
- I WAS, UH--
- TAKE YOUR FOOT OFF THE BRAKE.
PUT IT ON THE GAS.
AND LET OUT ON THE CLUTCH--
EASY.
OH, MY GOD, GIRL, EASY--
UGH, THAT'S EASY?
- MY SHOE--
THE HARD PART
OF DRIVING STICK IS TRYING
TO CONCENTRATE ON
THE CLUTCH AND THE THING.
- ALL RIGHT,
SO I'M TAKING YOU NOW.
'CAUSE THAT WAS BRUTAL.
- [laughs sarcastically]
- [grunts]
- WHAT'S IN THAT?
I ALWAYS, LIKE, PACK INSIDE--
- YEAH, I DON'T KNOW.
THERE'S, LIKE, STUFF FROM
YOUR LAST TRIP OR SOMETHING.
- UH--
- I DON'T KNOW.
AAH!
JESUS CH--
- [laughing]
- POOR BABY.
[high-pitched voice]
WHAT ARE WE DOING IN THERE?
IT'S OKAY.
WE'RE LEAVING HIM.
- SHOULD I JUST START LOOKING
FOR A NEW GIRLFRIEND NOW?
OR--
- NO, YOU CAN WAIT
A COUPLE WEEKS.
- ANYTHING ELSE
I SHOULD KNOW?
- UM, I'M PREGNANT.
- RIGHT.
I KNOW THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I TRY TO HAVE SEX WITH YOU
SIX TIMES A DAY
AND I GET DENIED CONSTANTLY.
- SAVING IT FOR
MY NEW BOYFRIEND.
- LET'S BREAK UP
FOR, LIKE, 15 MINUTES.
AND THEN WE'LL HAVE
MAKE UP SEX BEFORE YOU GO.
AND WE'LL GET BACK TOGETHER.
- NO, I GOT MY PERIOD.
- UGH!
- WE'RE GONNA BE TIGHT.
- OKAY, WELL, I HAVE
THREE MORE LUGGAGES.
CAN WE FIX IT?
WANT ME TO GO IN?
I'LL GO IN.
- I'LL GET IT.
YOU'RE GONNA HURT YOURSELF.
- MY TRUCK IS DEFINITELY
FOR NORMAL SIZE PEOPLE,
OVER, LIKE, 5'5".
- [laughs] WILL YOU
GET YOUR HANDS OFF MY ASS?
- NO, AND I'LL PULL YOU
BACK OUT.
GOD.
LIKE, LEGIT, WE LOOK LIKE
LITTLE [bleep]
TRYING TO PACK MY TRUCK
RIGHT NOW.
THAT'S SOME [bleep]
PROBLEMS FOR YOU.
- [sighs]
- YOU NERVOUS?
- YEAH.
- HOLY [bleep].
DID YOU JUST HEAR THAT?
ALL THE WEIGHT IN YOUR TRUNK
JUST MADE
MY REAR END BOTTOM OUT.
THAT WAS MY TIRE.
IF THAT RIPPED MY TIRE UP,
I'M GONNA FLIP OUT.
- [chuckles]
THIS IS CRAZY.
GOD IS SAYING
EVERY WHICH WAY,
"DON'T [bleep] GO LIVE
WITH A PREGNANT CHICK."
[hip-hop music]
* *
YAY, WE'RE HOME.
HONEY, I'M HOME!
IS SHE HERE?
NICOLE!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
WITH EVERYTHING THAT
HAPPENED TODAY,
I MAKE IT BEFORE NICOLE.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
- [burps]
- JENNI'S NOT SO MUCH
A HANDS-ON GIRL, YOU KNOW?
THANK GOD SHE'S GOT
A HANDS-ON BOYFRIEND.
- IT'S A LOT OF WORK,
MOVING.
- I KNOW.
LET'S GO GET THE REST OF IT.
YO!
HOW DID I NOT KNOW
THAT WAS YOU?
- HI.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- MWAH.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD. HOW ARE YOU?
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
I LIKE YOUR CAR, IT'S THE FIRST
TIME I'VE SEEN IT.
WHERE'S JIONNI?
- HOME.
- SO IT MEANS I GOTTA BRING
ALL YOUR [bleep] IN TOO?
- CAN YOU?
- OH, MY GOD.
- I WAS SO SCARED TO ASK JENNI,
BUT NOW YOU CAN.
ARE YOU GONNA DO IT NOW?
- UH, YEAH, YEAH.
- HELLO?
- YOU'RE HERE?
- FINALLY.
- DID JIONNI COME WITH YOU?
- NO.
- NO?
- THIS IS A BAD PREGNANCY DAY.
- OH, I'M DEFINITELY CALLING
JIONNI WHEN I GET OUT HERE.
I'M GONNA REAM HIM
OUT [bleep].
- I THINK ROGER'S
A LITTLE ANNOYED
BECAUSE JIONNI'S NOT HERE
TO HELP HIM WITH THE LUGGAGE.
BUT, UM, YOU KNOW,
[bleep] HAPPENS.
I TOLD JENNI,
SHE SHOULD GET PREGNANT,
BECAUSE THEN WE COULD
BE PREGNANT TOGETHER.
- OH, MY GOD.
- HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THAT?
- NOW YOU'RE SCARING ME.
I MEAN, YOUR SPERM
IS GETTING REALLY OLD.
SO YOU SHOULD JUST
DO IT SOON.
I FEEL LIKE THERE'S
A CERTAIN AGE
WHERE YOUR SPERM WON'T WORK
AND PREGNANT SOMEONE.
- WOW.
- SO I FEEL LIKE
HE SHOULD GET ON THAT.
- YOU'D HAVE TO CONVINCE
THIS GIRL
TO LET ME PUT MY PENIS
ANYWHERE NEAR HER
BEFORE WE COULD
HAVE A CHILD.
SHE'S ANTI-SEX.
- I'M ANTI-SEX NOW TOO.
- ARE YOU REALLY?
- WE HAVEN'T HAD SEX
IN, LIKE, A WEEK.
AND THAT'S LONG FOR US.
- WE'RE GOING ON JUST OVER
A YEAR NOW.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
- [laughs]
THAT'S MY CUE
TO GET OUT OF HERE.
- OKAY.
- ALL RIGHT, BABE,
I LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU.
- I LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU TOO.
- [grunts]
BYE, NICOLE.
TAKE CARE--
I WOULD SAY,
"TAKE CARE OF MY GIRL."
BUT I THINK MY GIRL'S GONNA
BE TAKING CARE OF YOU.
- SERIOUSLY.
- BYE.
- BYE. THANK YOU.
- NO PROBLEM.
- MY BOOBS HURT.
- I'M SURE THAT'S NOT GONNA
BE THE LAST TIME I HEAR THAT.
- THEY FEEL LIKE MILK DUDS.
DID YOU BRING TOWELS?
- I BROUGHT ONE.
- I GOT FOUR.
- WHO ARE YOU?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- I DON'T KNOW WHO
I JUST MOVED IN WITH.
OH, MY GOD.
- WHAT?
- EITHER MY DOG [bleep],
OR THAT DISHWASHER REEKS.
- EW, IT DOES SMELL
LIKE POOP.
- THERE'S A TURD
IN MY BEDROOM!
- STOP!
AND IT STARTS.
- OH, NO.
[sniffing]
- OH, MY GOD, THEY PEED
AND I'M PLAYING WITH IT.
[squealing]
I MEAN, I'M A VET TECH,
SO I'VE GOT [bleep] ON ME
ALL THE TIME--AND PISS.
BUT, I MEAN, COME ON.
IT'S THE FIRST NIGHT.
ANNOYING.
- NOW I GOTTA GO
CARRY A TURD
HALFWAY ACROSS
THE [bleep]--
- NO, THE GARBAGE IS RIGHT HERE.
- NO, BUT I WANNA FLUSH IT.
- WELL, THIS IS FUN.
- IT'S BEEN A LONG DAY.
IT'S BEEN, LIKE, A REALLY
[bleep] LONG DAY.
AND I'M CALLING IT A NIGHT
RIGHT NOW.
AND SO IS NICOLE.
LIKE, I'M OVER IT.
YAY, WE MOVED IN.
IT'S TIME TO PASS OUT.
- BYE.
- MWAH.
[laughter]
- THERE'S MORE SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW
ON THE WAY.
AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
[dog barking]
- UGH.
- WE'RE UP.
- IT'S OFFICIALLY, LIKE,
THE FIRST DAY IN THE NEW HOUSE.
AND THE DOGS WAKE ME UP
AT, LIKE, 7:00 IN THE MORNING.
I'M LIKE, "IF THIS HAPPENS
EVERY SINGLE MORNING,
I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN DO IT."
- MORNING.
- NO OFFENSE, BUT I WANTED
TO PUNCH THEM OUT,
LIKE, 20 MINUTES AGO.
- THAT WAS MY BAD.
- SO TODAY
IS JENNI'S BIRTHDAY.
YOU KNOW,
I DON'T HAVE THE CAKE.
I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO REALLY GIVE HER.
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
WE JUST MOVED IN.
AND ALL WE HAVE IS BAGELS.
* HAPPY BIRTHDAY *
- [laughs]
- I WAS GONNA GET YOU
A CUPCAKE,
BUT I DIDN'T GET
ANY CUPCAKES.
- AWW.
- MAKE A WISH.
WHAT'S YOUR FIRST
WISH TODAY?
THANKS, BOO.
- AWW.
MWAH.
I LOVE YOU.
- THAT WAS SWEET.
[techno music]
* *
- EW, IT STILL SMELLS
LIKE POOP OVER HERE.
THE BOYS ARE COMING OVER
TONIGHT,
SO WE WANNA CLEAN THE HOUSE
AND, UH,
MAKE SURE EVERYTHING
IS AT LEAST
NORMAL LOOKING
FOR THE BOYS.
- [gasps]
[laughs]
JENNI!
- YEAH?
- I'M AN IDIOT.
- [grunts]
- IT SMELLS LIKE POOP
IN HERE.
- OH, MY GOD, SO HEAVY.
- I THINK WE COULD DO IT
IN AN HOUR,
ME AND YOU.
- I'M STUCK.
- MAYBE NOT.
- IF THAT'S AN ANIMAL,
I'M NOT TOUCHING IT.
OH, MY GOD. OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD.
I TOUCHED IT.
WHAT NEXT?
- OKAY, I THINK WE'RE GOOD.
[rock music]
* *
[knock at door]
- WHO IS IT?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
WHO IS IT?
- EW, ROGER.
WHERE'S JIONNI?
- OH, DID I BUM YOU OUT?
I'M SORRY.
DO I STILL GET A KISS?
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
- YOU HAVE MY BRA?
[dogs barking]
- I THINK THAT'S JIONNI.
HELLO, ROGER.
PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- HOW ARE YOU, SIR?
- LET'S GO.
GRAB SOMETHING.
- OOH, [bleep].
I ALMOST JUST
BROKE THE BOOZE.
- JENNI, GOT YOU A CAKE.
- AWW.
- [cheers]
- LIKE IT?
- IT'S NICE.
- BABY, YOU WANT A DRINK?
- MAKE ME A--
WHAT DO YOU GOT?
- I'LL MAKE YOU
A STIFF ONE.
YOU WANT A SHIRLEY TEMPLE?
- YES, PLEASE.
- FOR SHIRLEY.
- HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
- TO THE THREE OF US DRINKING.
- WHERE'S MY SHIRLEY TEMPLE,
BITCHES?
- LISTEN--
- YOUR KID HAS ZERO CHANCE
OF BEING A PROFESSIONAL
BASKETBALL PLAYER.
- OH, YEAH.
- [laughing]
- ZERO.
- NICOLE.
- ROGER, SHUT UP.
- I'M BEING HONEST.
I'M BEING HONEST.
- YEAH, I MEAN,
ROGER ALWAYS GOES THERE.
BUT, YOU KNOW, DON'T FREAKING
TALK ABOUT MY BABY.
I'LL [bleep] SLICE
YOUR PENIS OFF.
- IF YOUR KID'S TALL,
I'LL TAKE A PATERNITY TEST.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
- [laughs]
- ROGER, I HOPE YOU
HAVE A KID LIKE SIMON BIRCH,
YOU [bleep].
OH, THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
- I LOOK LIKE A MOM.
THIS IS MY LIFE NOW.
COOL.
- READY FOR
THE BACHELOR PARTY?
- [laughs]
YOU BETTER--YOU BETTER
START ASKING FOR PERMISSION
RIGHT NOW.
FOR ME, NOT FOR YOU.
JENNI, I'M PUTTING IN
AN OFFICIAL REQUEST RIGHT NOW
FOR JIONNI'S BACHELOR PARTY.
- IT'S IN VEGAS.
- NO.
- BUT WE'RE GONNA
BE IN VEGAS TOO.
- JENNI?
- WHAT?
- CAN ROGER COME?
- SEE THAT?
THAT'S REAL LIFE RIGHT THERE.
WHAT IS IT THAT
BOTHERS YOU SO IF I WENT?
LIKE, WHY WOULD IT
BE A BIG DEAL?
- I DON'T WANT SOME GIRL
SHOVING HER [bleep]
IN YOUR FACE.
- SEE?
- I KNOW WHAT GOES DOWN
AT BACHELOR PARTIES.
I DON'T LIKE IT.
I DON'T WANT NO DIRTY SKANK
GRINDING ON HIM
AT JIONNI'S BACHELOR PARTY.
NO OFFENSE.
- UGH.
WELL, NO OFFENSE?
I DON'T WANT ANYONE
GRINDING ON MY MAN EITHER.
- GUYS GET GRIMY ASS STRIPPERS
COMING
TO THEIR BACHELOR PARTY.
- SEE?
- I'M SUPPOSED TO BE LIKE,
"OH, YOU'RE GOING THERE
AND YOU'RE NOT GONNA
HAVE [bleep] IN YOUR FACE."
THERE IS NOTHING GOOD THAT
COMES FROM BACHELOR PARTIES.
PEOPLE GET DIVORCES BEFORE
THEY GET MARRIED
ON BACHELOR PARTIES.
LIKE, WEDDINGS DON'T HAPPEN
BECAUSE OF BACHELOR PARTIES.
- [bleep] PARANOIA.
- WHY IS THAT PARANOIA?
- FORGET I ASKED.
- THAT'S--THAT'S TRUTH.
THAT'S FACTS.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO [bleep]
OUT TO THE DINER
AND HANGING OUT AND
GETTING A CLASS OF ORANGE JUICE.
- IF THAT HAPPENED TO YOU--
IT COMES DOWN
TO TRUST, FOR STARTERS.
- IT DOESN'T MATTER.
IT'S STILL DISRESPECT.
- COMES DOWN TO TRUST.
- JENNI'S A PSYCHO BITCH
FOR A GIRLFRIEND.
SHE'S JUST LIKE, "ROGER,
YOU'RE NOT DOING ANYTHING.
"YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO THE BAR.
YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO ANY BACHELOR PARTIES."
YOU KNOW, I KIND OF FEEL BAD
FOR ROGER.
- IT'S THE DISRESPECT.
- DISRESPECT TO WHO?
- I'M ALLOWING--
- TO ME.
- BUT I WOULDN'T HAVE
A PROBLEM WITH YOU DOING IT.
- IT'S NOT GONNA BE FOR
ANOTHER YEAR AND A HALF.
WE'RE NOT GETTING MARRIED
FOR AWHILE.
- I NEED TO WORK ON THIS
[bleep] FOR A YEAR AND A HALF.
- JENNI, YOU'LL BE
ENGAGED BY THEN.
- IF THIS KEEPS UP LIKE THIS,
SHE WON'T BE.
- I MEAN, SHE LOVES YOU.
- WHY ARE YOU
COOL WITH IT THEN?
- BECAUSE HE WOULD LEAVE ME
IF I WAS LIKE THAT.
- [laughing]
- SORRY, JENNI.
- YOU'RE PREGNANT?
I HAVEN'T REALLY TALKED TO
ANYONE THAT HAS BEEN PREGNANT.
DOES YOUR VAGINA RIP
TO YOUR BUTT HOLE?
- YEAH, I MEAN, IT CAN.
- UGH!
- YOU READY TO GO
GET YOUR BELLY LOOKED AT?
- TONIGHT I HAVE
MY DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT,
AND I'M JUST SO NERVOUS.
- IT'S MOVING?
- IT'S MOVING.
- THIS REAL.
- EW!