- I AM NOT OKAY IN THIS
RELATIONSHIP AT THIS POINT.
- YOU SHOULD BE WITH TOM.
YOU GUYS WERE PERFECT
FOR EACH OTHER.
- BY TELLING ME THAT
I SHOULD BE WITH MY EX,
YOU CAN GO [bleep] YOURSELF.
- THEY'RE ALL OVER HIM.
I'M, LIKE, QUESTIONING
OUR ENGAGEMENT.
LIKE, ARE YOU READY?
- I THOUGHT MAYBE YOU
WERE READY
TO BE A MOTHER AND A WIFE.
MAYBE YOU'RE NOT.
- THAT WAS MEAN.
[Icona Pop's I Love It ]
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT
I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
- WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
- [crying] HE SAID
I'M NOT READY TO BE A MOM.
- YOU'RE NOT READY
TO BE ONE?
- IT'S A LOW BLOW
FOR JIONNI TO SAY
I'M NOT READY TO BE A MOM.
YOU DON'T SAY THAT.
- DO THEY THINK IT'S ALL RIGHT
TO, LIKE, SAY THESE THINGS?
THAT'S LIKE ROGER SAYING
I ONLY
DESERVE TO BE WITH MY EX.
[phone ringing]
- HELLO.
- WHY YOU HANGING UP ON ME?
THAT'S REAL MATURE.
TALK IT OVER.
- NO, DON'T--DON'T SAY
I'M NOT READY TO BE A MOM.
IT'S NOT TRUE AT ALL.
- HEY, I DIDN'T
DO ONE BAD THING TO YOU
FOR YOU TO SAY I'M NOT READY
FOR AN ENGAGEMENT.
MY LITTLE COUSIN ASKED
ME TO TAKE A PICTURE--
- WELL, WHICH ONE'S
YOUR LITTLE COUSIN THEN?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- [snorts]
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THIS PICTURE IS, NICOLE.
- CAN I SEND IT TO YOU?
BECAUSE WHEN I SEE
[bleep] LIKE THAT, IT'S LIKE,
I DON'T WANNA BE ENGAGED
TO SOMEONE THAT [bleep]
DOES THAT AND TAKES PICTURES
WITH RANDOM GIRLS.
- IF I EVER WERE TO SAY
I'M THINKING TWICE
ABOUT THIS ENGAGEMENT,
IT WOULDN'T BE
FOR YOU TO SEND
A PICTURE WITH A GUY.
IT WOULD BE
YOU CHEATING ON ME.
THOSE ARE HARSH,
HARSH WORDS.
STOP TRYING TO BE
A [bleep] TOUGH ASS.
YOU WANNA GET MAD AT ME?
FINE.
I TOOK A PICTURE WITH SOMEBODY
WHO WANTED
TO TAKE A PICTURE WITH ME.
I'M SORRY.
I'M VERY, VERY SORRY FOR THAT.
- YEAH, I'M GONNA BE MAD
AT THAT, BECAUSE YOU KNOW
I HATE IT.
- IT WILL NOT HAPPEN AGAIN.
NICOLE, WHEN I'M DONE TALKING,
THEN YOU CAN TALK.
- OKAY, DAD.
- ALL RIGHT, I TOOK
A [bleep] PICTURE
WITH A--WITH A RANDOM GIRL,
VERY SORRY.
IT WILL NEVER HAPPEN AGAIN.
- YOU SAID IT WAS
YOUR COUSIN.
- WHAT?
- YOU SAID YOU TOOK A PICTURE
WITH YOUR COUSIN.
- I--IT COULD'VE BEEN THAT,
YEAH.
- I AM PRAYING TO THE GODS
RIGHT NOW
THAT JIONNI DIDN'T CHEAT.
BECAUSE HE'S, LIKE,
MY WHOLE LIFE RIGHT NOW.
SO IF HE CHEATED, ME AND MY BABY
ARE GOING AWAY.
- MY DAY'S RUINED.
MY FIANCÉE,
WHO'S HOLDING MY BABY,
IS QUESTIONING
MY ENGAGEMENT WITH HER.
DO YOU WANNA BE WITH ME?
- YEAH, I WANNA BE WITH
SOMEONE THAT
DOESN'T WANT OTHER GIRLS.
[crying]
- I DON'T WANT OTHER GIRLS,
NICOLE, LIKE, WHAT--
- [sniffling]
- YOU'RE MAKING ME OUT
TO BE THE BAD GUY,
AND I'M NOT.
- NO, I'M NOT.
I'M JUST TELLING YOU
HOW I FEEL.
[sniffling]
- STOP--STOP CRYING.
I DON'T LIKE YOU UPSET.
- I'M A VERY EMOTIONAL
PREGNANT LADY RIGHT NOW.
AND WHEN I SEE PICTURES
OF HIM WITH, YOU KNOW,
YOUNG, PRETTY GIRLS,
I'M LIKE, YOU KNOW,
"DOES HE MISS BEING SINGLE
AND, YOU KNOW,
"MEETING OTHER GIRLS,
OR IS HE TOTALLY FINE
WITH ME FOR THE REST
OF HIS LIFE?"
- I ASKED YOU TO GET MARRIED
TO YOU FOR A [bleep] REASON.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
I WANNA BE WITH.
YOU'RE THE ONLY WOMAN I WANNA
HAVE MORE KIDS WITH.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
I WANNA LIVE WITH.
SORRY I-I TOOK
A [bleep] PICTURE.
I'M VERY SORRY.
I'LL NEVER DO IT AGAIN,
OKAY?
BUT JUST THINK ABOUT
WHAT YOU SAID TO ME.
YOU RUINED MY WHOLE
ENTIRE [bleep] BIRTHDAY.
MY WHOLE BIRTHDAY, OKAY?
HELLO?
- HERE.
- OKAY?
I'LL TALK TO YOU LATER.
- WHAT IS WRONG WITH THEM?
- I THINK THEY'RE CRAZY.
- RIGHT NOW, IT FEELS
LIKE COUPLES HELL.
I MEAN, ME AND JIONNI
ARE FIGHTING.
AND ROGER AND JENNI,
THEY DON'T KNOW, YOU KNOW,
IF THEY'RE GONNA
BE TOGETHER OR BREAK UP.
AND I JUST WANNA
CURL IN A BALL AND DIE.
WELL, NOT DIE,
BUT SLEEP FOREVER.
- WHAT A [bleep]
DEPRESSING DAY.
I FEEL LIKE [bleep]
THIS MORNING.
I'M NOT GETTING OVER WHAT
ROGER SAID TO ME THAT NIGHT.
AND I DON'T KNOW
IF WE SHOULD BE TOGETHER.
- * LOST IN THIS PLACE *
* YOU CAN'T FIND
THE DOOR TO LEAVE *
[phone ringing]
- [whispering]
I'M COMING. I'M COMING.
[phone ringing]
GET THE [bleep] OUT OF HERE.
ROGER'S CALLING IN.
I LITERALLY WANNA CRY.
WHAT'S UP?
- JUST GOT OUT OF WORK.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU
HAVE PLANS OR NOT,
BUT I WOULD LIKE
TO COME UP THERE
SO THAT WE CAN
GET TO THE BOTTOM
OF YOUR ISSUES.
JENNI'S EXTREMELY ANGRY
WITH ME.
I'M PRETTY UPSET MYSELF.
SO I DECIDED, YOU KNOW WHAT,
I'M GONNA GO THERE.
I NEED TO SEE YOU
EYE-TO-EYE AND--
AND FIGURE OUT
WHERE WE STAND.
I WILL HEAD UP THERE
AFTER I SHOWER.
AND I'LL SEE YOU
IN A COUPLE HOURS.
- NO.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN NO?
- I DON'T KNOW
IF I WANNA SEE YOU.
- CURRENTLY STILL
YOUR BOYFRIEND.
YOU HAVING ISSUES--
- OH, YOU ARE? YOU ARE?
'CAUSE IT DOESN'T
SEEM LIKE IT.
I DON'T DESERVE
TO BE WITH YOU, REMEMBER?
I DESERVE TO BE WITH TOM.
I AM THE MOST INSECURE
PERSON IN THE WORLD.
- BECAUSE YOU DON'T ADMIT--
- WILL YOU [bleep] LISTEN TO ME?
BECAUSE OUR RELATIONSHIP
IS BASICALLY
ON A [bleep] THREAD RIGHT NOW.
I DO NOT NEED TO HEAR THAT
FROM MY [bleep] BOYFRIEND
OF TWO YEARS,
BREAKING ME DOWN,
SAYING THAT I AM ONLY WORTH
ENOUGH TO BE WITH
A PIECE OF [bleep] LIKE TOM
AND NOT GOOD ENOUGH
TO BE WITH YOU.
DO YOU KNOW HOW THAT
MAKES ME FEEL COMING FROM--
I WOULD'VE RATHER HAD
MY JAW SMASHED
IN A THOUSAND PIECES.
YOU WERE A [bleep]
[bleep] TO ME.
AND YOU HAVE BEEN.
AND THAT'S WHY
I WON'T TALK TO YOU.
- OKAY, THAT'S FINE.
- AND THAT'S WHY I'M NOT--
I'M NOT INTRIGUED
TO SEE YOU TONIGHT.
- WHEN I FEEL ATTACKED,
I GO ON THE DEFENSE,
AND I [bleep] WIN.
- THE ONLY THING
YOU'RE WINNING AT, ROGER,
IS LOSING ME.
- BEFORE WE DECIDE
WHICH DIRECTION WE'RE GOING,
I WOULD LIKE TO SPEAK TO YOU.
SEE YOU IN A COUPLE HOURS.
- NO.
- I'M ON MY WAY.
THERE ARE CERTAIN THINGS THAT
I WILL FIGHT ABOUT EVERY TIME,
THAT I'LL STAND MY GROUND ON
AND YOU CAN'T BULLY ME OVER,
IT WON'T HAPPEN.
I'LL SEE YOU IN A COUPLE HOURS.
- WHY?
- I'M ON MY WAY.
- UGH. GOD.
- GET OVER IT, OR NOT!
- I'M NOT GETTING INTO THIS!
- I DIDN'T WANNA
GET INTO THIS!
YOU WANTED TO GET INTO THIS!
- SO [bleep] STOP!
- ROGER AND JENNI
ARE SCREAMING OUTSIDE,
AND I'M HONESTLY SCARED.
[ Give Me a Chance
by The Miracals]
- * GIVE ME A CHANCE *
- NOT EVEN CLOSE TO LOOKING
LIKE A HUMAN BEING.
- * I WILL LOVE YOU FOREVER *
* I'LL NEVER GO
I'LL NEVER GO *
- ROUND TWO WITH MIGRAINE.
[doorbell ringing repeatedly]
- OH, MY GOD,
NOT WITH THE [bleep] BELL.
- HEY.
- HELLO.
I DON'T WANNA SEE HIM
AT THIS POINT.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW IF I WANNA
BE WITH HIM AT THIS POINT.
LIKE, I HAVE, LIKE, NO FEELINGS
IN ME RIGHT NOW, NOTHING.
- WHERE ARE WE AT?
WHAT DO YOU WANNA DO?
- YOU WANT ME
TO ANSWER THAT WHEN
MY BLOOD IS BOILING
RIGHT NOW?
- YEAH. IF WE'RE DONE,
I'M COOL, JUST SAY IT.
- YOU'RE--YOU'RE COOL
WITH IT IF WE'RE DONE,
'CAUSE YOU HAVE OBVIOUSLY
NO FEELINGS TOWARDS ME.
- THAT'S NOT WHAT I SAID.
- BUT NO, YOU'RE ACTING LIKE IT.
- I DO NOT WANT
TO BE WITH SOMEBODY
WHO DOESN'T WANT
TO BE WITH ME.
I WOULD NEVER WANT
TO DO THAT.
IF YOU DO NOT WANT
TO BE WITH ME, JENNI,
THEN I HAVE NO OPTION,
BUT TO MOVE ON.
HEY, LET'S BE ADULTS.
I MEAN, YOU WOULD AGREE
THIS ISN'T WORKING OUT, RIGHT?
YOU WOULD AGREE THAT
YOU'RE UNHAPPY, CORRECT?
- OH, SO THIS IS WHERE
THE BREAKUP'S COMING?
- WELL, I'M JUST SAYING,
LET'S GET TO THE BOTTOM OF THIS.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA SIT HERE
AND GO BACK AND FORTH ALL DAY?
- I'M PISSED OFF,
AND I DON'T LIKE YOU.
THAT IS CORRECT.
- OKAY.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT
ME TO DO?
- [scoffs]
- YOU SHOULD HAVE AN ANSWER
FOR THAT QUESTION.
IT'S NOT THAT DIFFICULT
OF A QUESTION.
- WHY DO I HAVE TO HAVE
THE PRESSURE
PUT ON ME THAT I HAVE TO--
- BECAUSE YOU'RE THE ONE
WITH THE ISSUE,
AND YOU'RE THE ONE
THAT'S UNHAPPY.
- I ONLY HAVE
ONE ISSUE WITH YOU.
YOU'RE A [bleep] [bleep].
- I AM NOT APOLOGIZING
FOR SATURDAY.
ACCEPT IT OR DON'T.
- JEEZ, IT'S LIKE, WHAT DO YOU
[bleep] WANT, ROGER?
- EITHER GET OVER IT,
OR NOT!
- I'M NOT GETTING INTO THIS!
- I DIDN'T WANNA GET INTO THIS!
YOU WANTED TO GET INTO THIS!
- SO [bleep] STOP!
- YOU GET OVER IT!
- ROGER AND JENNI
ARE SCREAMING OUTSIDE,
AND I'M HONESTLY SCARED
BECAUSE ROGER,
WHEN HE RAISES HIS VOICE,
HE SOUNDS LIKE
A TYRANNOSAURUS REX THAT
JUST WANTS TO EAT EVERYONE.
AND RIGHT NOW,
I HAVE TO PEE SO BAD
THAT I JUST WANT THEM
TO STOP FIGHTING,
OR GO IN ANOTHER ROOM,
SO I CAN RUN
TO THE BATHROOM REAL QUICK.
- YOU CAN'T SEE THAT
YOU HURT MY FEELINGS?
- I NEVER SAID I DIDN'T
HURT YOUR FEELINGS.
- THAT'S WHAT I'M TRYING
TO SAY, ROGER.
- I NEVER SAID THAT
I DIDN'T.
BUT I DON'T FEEL LIKE
I OWE YOU AN APOLOGY
BECAUSE I DID SOMETHING WRONG.
- I TOLD YOU,
AN APOLOGY
ISN'T GOOD ENOUGH.
- I'M NOT GONNA BEAT THIS
[bleep] HORSE ANYMORE.
THIS SUCKER'S DEAD.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA
GET OVER IT.
I'M NOT GOING TO APOLOGIZE.
STALEMATE.
- WHAT?
- IT'S A STALEMATE.
- WHAT THE [bleep]
IS A STALEMATE?
COME ON, YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THE [bleep] STALEMATE IS.
I'M NOT JOKING RIGHT NOW.
I DON'T NEED TO HEAR
YOUR WEIRD PHRASES
OR YOUR SAYINGS.
GOD, YOU'RE OLD.
- I AM OLD.
YOU KEEP POINTING
THAT OUT CONSTANTLY.
AND I'M PROUD OF MY AGE.
I'D RATHER BE 36 THAN
WHAT I WAS AT 26,
ANY DAY OF THE WEEK.
[sighs]
MAYBE IT'S BECAUSE
OF OUR AGE,
I'M A LITTLE OLDER.
BUT I'VE BEEN WITH JENNI
ALMOST TWO YEARS NOW,
AND IT FEELS LIKE TEN.
WHAT WE BEEN THROUGH,
IT FEELS LIKE TEN.
- WHAT'S IT GONNA TAKE
FOR YOU TO, LIKE,
BREAK DOWN THESE
[bleep] PSYCHOTIC
DEFENSIVE WALLS
THAT YOU HAVE?
- WHAT'S IT GONNA TAKE
FOR YOU TO BE A SECURE WOMAN?
- NOT BEING WITH YOU.
- OKAY.
SO BE SINGLE.
BE SINGLE,
PULL THE TRIGGER.
- I JUST NEED TO MAKE SURE
THAT THE DECISION
IS WHAT I REALLY WANT.
[slow music]
* *
- I DON'T WANNA LEAVE
THIS RELATIONSHIP, JENNI.
I DON'T WANT TO.
BUT I'M NOT GOING
TO BE ACCUSED
OF BEING THIS HORRIBLE
BOYFRIEND THAT I'M NOT.
I'M NOT A HORRIBLE BOYFRIEND.
- * ALL WE HAD *
* AND ALL IS GONE *
- SO I'M SORRY IF I CAN'T
MAKE A DECISION IN JERSEY CITY.
BECAUSE MY DECISION AFFECTS ME
MORE THAN IT AFFECTS YOU.
YOU CAN GO BACK TO A LIFE...
- IT DOESN'T AFFECT YOUR--
- THAT YOU'VE HAD FOR 13 YEARS.
I DON'T.
- THAT'S SO MINISCULE COMPARED--
- IT ISN'T--
- COMPARED TO WHAT IT DOES
TO YOUR HEART AND MY HEART.
IT DOES THE SAME THING.
AND I'M ASKING YOU WHAT YOU NEED
TO MAKE THAT DECISION.
FOR ME TO LEAVE,
FOR ME TO GIVE YOU TIME, WHAT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- YOU CAN'T HELP
WHO YOU FALL IN LOVE WITH.
I FELL IN LOVE WITH JENNI.
[sniffling]
YOU CAN SAY WHAT YOU WANT,
YOU KNOW?
YOU CAN SAY
WE'RE NOT MEANT TO BE.
"THEY--THEY FIGHT TOO MUCH."
IT'S TRUE.
BUT, I JUST WANT IT TO WORK,
YOU KNOW?
- LIKE I SAID BEFORE,
I MEAN,
I DON'T LIKE YOU.
I DON'T LIKE US.
- I DON'T LIKE YOU.
- OH, OKAY.
OTHER THAN THE NAME CALLING
AND RIDICULING--
AND I LOOK YOU IN THE EYE
AND SINCERELY APOLOGIZE
FOR THAT.
I LOST MY TEMPER.
I DIDN'T HAVE THE RIGHT
TO SAY CERTAIN THINGS
THAT I SAID.
BUT I WILL NEVER FEEL
LIKE I DID ANYTHING WRONG
SATURDAY NIGHT.
- I LOVE YOU WITH
ALL MY HEART.
I INVESTED SO MUCH,
OBVIOUSLY, FOR A REASON.
THAT REASON IS A LITTLE LOST
TO ME RIGHT NOW,
AND I'M TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
IF I CAN FIND IT AGAIN.
I'M SAD ABOUT IT,
BECAUSE I DON'T LIKE HIM.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S
GONNA WORK OUT.
I DON'T KNOW IF I'M JUST
SITTING HERE BUYING TIME.
BUT IN THE SAME SENSE,
I DON'T KNOW
IF I'M READY FOR
IT TO BE OVER RIGHT NOW.
- IT'S ODD, JENNI,
'CAUSE WE HAVE
TOTAL OPPOSITE POLAR MINDS,
YET THIS UNDENIABLE
ATTRACTION
FOR EACH OTHER.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE
GOD WAS LIKE,
"HERE YOU GO.
[bleep] YOU."
YOU KNOW?
- YEP.
- YOU CAN MAKE ME HAPPIER
THAN ANY PERSON ON THE PLANET.
AND YOU CAN PISS ME OFF
MORE THAN
I'VE EVER BEEN PISSED OFF
IN MY ENTIRE LIFE.
- I'D SAY THE SAME THING.
- I DON'T WANNA LEAVE YOU.
I DON'T WANT TO BE SINGLE.
I DON'T WANNA BE AN OLD HERMIT,
YOU KNOW, THAT LIVES ALONE.
I'D LIKE TO HAVE KIDS
ONE DAY.
I FEEL LIKE I HAVE A LOT
OF GOOD IN ME TO PASS ON.
YOU KNOW?
[grunts]
WHOEVER SAID,
"REAL MEN DON'T CRY,"
I WOULD LOVE TO SEE THAT
MOTHER[bleep] RIGHT NOW.
IT'S EITHER LET IT EAT US UP,
AND LET IT RUIN US,
AND WE DO SPLIT UP,
OR YOU LET IT GO,
AND I LET IT GO.
- I CAN LET IT GO, BUT
IT DOESN'T MEAN I CAN BE HAPPY.
- I'M RIGHT THERE WITH YA.
I'M RIGHT THERE WITH YA.
TRUST ME.
- MM-HMM.
THIS ARGUMENT
IS GOING IN CIRCLES,
AND NEITHER OF US
ARE BACKING DOWN.
BUT FOR WHATEVER REASON
WITH ROGER,
I JUST CAN'T FEEL LIKE
IT'S OVER YET.
I CAN'T TURN THAT
LIGHT SWITCH OFF.
ARE YOU GETTING AN EYE HEADACHE?
- MM-HMM.
- MY LEFT EYE'S BEEN POUNDING
FOR [bleep] SIX HOURS.
- I'LL BE HONEST WITH YOU,
JENNI, THE ONLY WAY
I COULD POSSIBLY LOVE YOU MORE
IS IF YOU WERE MUTE.
- [chuckles]
- THAT'S THE ONLY WAY.
- WHAT THE [bleep]?
IT'S NOT FUNNY.
I'M TRYING TO BE MAD AT YOU.
- IT WAS A PRETTY GOOD ONE,
ACTUALLY.
- PRICK.
ROGER MAKES ME LAUGH
AND THAT'S WHY I LOVE HIM.
BUT HE DRIVES ME
[bleep] NUTS.
- ARE YOU MAD AT ME?
- NO.
- ARE YOU MAD AT JIONNI?
- I'M PREGNANT.
I DON'T NEED THIS [bleep].
- I KNOW.
I'M SORRY YOU HAD
TO LISTEN TO ALL THAT.
[exhales]
- I THINK YOU SHOULD
CALL JIONNI.
- AND SAY WHAT?
- THAT HIS PREGNANT FIANCÉE IS
IN BED AND DEPRESSED OVER THIS.
- HE'S HEARTBROKEN BECAUSE--
- SO IS SHE.
- WHY CAN'T YOU CALL HIM?
I HATE GETTING INVOLVED
IN OTHER PEOPLE'S RELATIONSHIPS.
GOD KNOWS WE HAVE
ENOUGH ISSUES.
- IT'S 10:00 AT NIGHT.
OBVIOUSLY WE CAN'T
FIX OUR PROBLEMS.
BUT WE'RE ABLE
TO BE "GROWN-UPS"
AND GET AHOLD OF JIONNI
TO SAVE HIS BIRTHDAY.
I KNOW NICOLE'S
SAD IN BED.
AND I DON'T WANT HER
DEPRESSED PREGNANT.
IF SHE REALLY MISSES
JIONNI'S BIRTHDAY,
IT'S GONNA EAT HER ALIVE.
- HELLO?
- JIONNI, IT'S JENNI.
NICOLE HAS BEEN
SLEEPING ALL DAY.
I'M CONCERNED ABOUT HER.
SHE'S PROBABLY STARVING.
SHE HASN'T EATEN.
AND I THINK SHE'S VERY
DISTRAUGHT OVER WHAT HAPPENED.
MAYBE IF YOU CAME HERE,
SOMETHING COULD BE RESOLVED.
- JUST SAY IF HE DOESN'T
WANNA COME UP HERE,
WE COULD PROBABLY MAKE
THE LAST COUPLE HOURS
AT HEMINGWAY'S.
[laughs]
- SHE'S NUTS.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL COME THERE.
TELL ME YOU'LL
ANSWER THE DOOR.
- I'LL ANSWER, OR SHE WILL
IF I CAN GET HER UP.
- ALL RIGHT, I'LL BE THERE
IN A HALF HOUR.
- ALL RIGHT.
- THANKS, BYE.
- BYE.
I HAVE CRAMPS.
- AWESOME, NO SEX.
- I CALLED JIONNI.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU HEARD.
- YEAH, I WAS GONNA
CALL HIM ANYWAY.
BUT THANK YOU.
- I JUST TOLD HIM
TO GET HERE.
MAYBE WE CAN SALVAGE
HIS BIRTHDAY.
[ Pink Balloons
by Kari Kimmel]
- I FEEL LIKE
WE SHOULD GO OUT NOW.
MAYBE I OVERREACTED BECAUSE
HE JUST TURNED 25.
AND THAT'S, LIKE, A QUARTER
OF YOUR LIFE THAT YOU LIVED.
AND, UM, I'M AN [bleep],
AND I RUINED THAT.
SO I NEED TO FIX IT.
- * BRING ME A KISS *
* BRING ME THE SUN
AND MOON *
* MAYBE SOME ROSES *
* THAT WOULD BE NICE TOO *
- MY BOOBS ARE ENORMOUS.
- * AND I'LL BE YOUR
FAVORITE GIRL *
[doorbell rings]
- JIONNI'S HERE, NICOLE.
- PUP?
- HI.
- I'M SORRY.
- WHY ARE YOU ALL DRESSED UP?
- 'CAUSE IT'S YOUR BIRTHDAY.
- * AND WE WILL
FALL IN LOVE *
- I'M SORRY.
- I WALK IN, THE FIRST
THING NICOLE SAYS
IS, "I'M SORRY."
THAT FACT THAT SHE SAID
SORRY TO ME
IS WHY I LOVE HER, AND
IS WHY WE'RE A STRONG COUPLE,
AND IS WHY SHE'S AMAZING.
- ARE YOU MAD AT ME?
- NO, I'M NOT MAD AT YOU.
[door shuts]
- YOU LOOK CUTE.
- THERE'S MORE SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW
ON THE WAY,
AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
- JIONNI, LOOK.
- OH, YEAH, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
LET'S SEE THIS PICTURE.
- HERE IT IS, REAL QUICK.
- THIS IS THE GIRL
YOU SAID LOOKED NICE.
LOOK, THEY'RE TOUCHING YOU
WITH THEIR SKINS.
- THAT'S A REAL NICE DRESS.
AW, MAN.
I WOULD BE MAD TOO
IF MY COUSIN
IS IN THE BACKGROUND
IN THE MIDDLE.
- [laughs]
- I'D BE--I'D BE REALLY MAD.
- I NEVER MET HER.
- MY COUS--
- YOU DON'T HAVE
ANY BLONDE COUSINS.
- SHE LIVES DOWN THE SHORE.
- GOD, YOU TWO ARE THE MOST
INSECURE HUMAN BEINGS
EVER TO WALK THE FACE
OF THE EARTH, EVER.
- YOU GUYS ARE, LIKE,
HOLDING HANDS.
THAT'S NOT YOUR COUSIN THOUGH.
LOOK, YOU'RE TOUCHING.
- HOW'D I GET CALLED INSECURE?
THIS ENTIRE FIGHT
WAS OVER A PICTURE
OF MY COUSIN AND HER FRIENDS.
REALLY?
- CAN I HAVE A CAB
TO [bleep] STREET
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE FOR
FOUR PEOPLE TO POWERHOUSE?
- YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
- * IF YOU THINK THAT
I'D FORGIVE YOU *
* WITHOUT ANY THOUGHT *
* AND THAT I'D HOLD YOUR HAND
AND KISS YOUR ASS *
* AND JUST BLOW IT OFF *
* YOU'RE SMOKING CRACK *
* IF YOU THINK
I'LL TAKE IT BACK *
[vocalizing]
- THREE LEMON DROP SHOTS
AND ONE PICKLE JUICE.
- IS IT REALLY?
- YEP.
- TAKING SHOTS OF PICKLE JUICE
IS BETTER
THAN DOING THE REAL THING
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
YOU KINDA GET
A LITTLE HAPPY,
AND THEN YOU DON'T GET
A HANGOVER THE NEXT DAY.
- HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
- HAPPY BIRTHDAY, PUP.
- THANK YOU.
TO US FOUR
BEING BACK TOGETHER.
- YEAH.
SEE HOW LONG THIS LASTS.
- TO THROWING
ANOTHER ONE BACK, PAL.
- THANK YOU.
HAPPY 25TH, MOTHER[bleep].
- JENNI, IF YOU GET DRUNK,
WILL ROGER GET LUCKY TONIGHT?
- NEVER, DUDE, THERE'S
ZERO CHANCE OF ME GETTING LAID.
- WHAT ARE THE CHANCES
OF ROGER GETTING LUCKY?
- ZERO.
- HE'S SLEEPING ON THE COUCH.
- I DON'T EVEN HAVE TO LOOK.
I KNOW ON ANY GIVEN NIGHT
THE CHANCE
OF ME GETTING LAID IS ZERO.
- I'M REALLY OVER THE FACT
THAT ROGER
DOESN'T GET SEX FROM JIONNI.
[laughter]
I DIDN'T MEAN THAT.
I ALWAYS, LIKE, MIX UP
JENNI AND JIONNI,
'CAUSE THEY'RE BOTH "J"s.
[laughter]
- YOU CAN TELL
WHERE YOUR HEAD'S AT.
- WHAT WAS IT AGAIN?
- ROGER'S GETTING LAID.
- NO. NO CHANCE, BRO,
NO CHANCE.
I HAVE A BETTER CHANCE,
HONESTLY,
OF NEGOTIATING A [bleep]
GAY DEAL WITH YOU
IN THE BATHROOM
THAN I DO WITH HER.
- THAT'S A VERY GOOD SHOT.
[laughter]
- I LOVE YOU.
- AH-HA.
- WHOO-HOO!
[cheers and applause]
all: HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
- HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
[laughs]
HE'S SO MAD.
- CATCH MY HAIR ON FIRE.
- PROUD OF YOU, BUDDY.
- WHY?
- 'CAUSE HE CAME UP HERE.
I DIDN'T THINK HE WAS COMING.
- I'M PROUD OF YOU TOO.
- I WASN'T COMING UP.
- DID IT TURN OUT
TO BE WORTH IT?
- YES.
- YEAH, 'CAUSE I DID
ALL YOUR DIRTY WORK.
- I WANTED TO COME UP.
- I THINK IT WOULD'VE
BEEN TOO MUCH,
TWO FIGHTS GOING ON
AT THE SAME TIME.
- I WOULDN'T HAVE
FOUGHT WITH HIM.
- AT ALL, PERIOD?
'CAUSE YOU TRUST HIM
AND YOU'RE SECURE?
- 'CAUSE I REALIZED I MAYBE
OVERREACTED A LITTLE BIT.
[laughter]
- I'M GLAD I CAME.
- ME TOO.
- I'M GLAD JENNI CALLED ME.
- I WAS GONNA CALL YOU!
ANNOYING.
- [mouthing]
NO, SHE WASN'T.
- FAKE BABY TIME.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT
GETTING NICOLE A FAKE BABY,
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE SHE SHOULD
PREP FOR MOTHERHOOD.
- IS THIS A [bleep] BABY?
EW, IT HAS A WIENER!
SO TODAY IS MY APPOINTMENT,
AND I'M VERY EXCITED
BECAUSE I'M GONNA
ASK THE DOCTOR
IF HE CAN TELL THE SEX.
CAN YOU SEE?
DO YOU GUYS WANNA
KNOW WHAT IT IS, OR--?
both: YEAH.