- MAAH!
[both screaming]
- AAH!
- EVER SINCE
WE MET EACH OTHER...
HELLO!
PARTY'S HERE. WHOO!
JENNI HAS BEEN
MY BEST FRIEND.
- DON'T TELL ANYBODY.
- NO ONE'S
LOOKING AT YOU.
- STOP IT!
SHE CAN LIFT MY SPIRIT
AT THE DROP OF A HAT.
[both squealing]
- SMELL MY FINGER.
- [laughing]
IF NICOLE NEEDS SOMETHING,
I'LL BE THERE FOR HER.
[overlapping shouts]
- [sobbing]
- IF I NEED SOMETHING,
SHE'LL BE THERE FOR ME.
BOO, IT'S LIKE AN EMERGENCY.
I HAVE TO GO HOME
AND GET MY DOGS.
WILL YOU TAKE THE DRIVE WITH ME?
- OF COURSE.
I WILL ALWAYS BE THERE
FOR JENNI NO MATTER WHAT.
- WE'RE GOING HOME.
- EVER SINCE WE MET EACH OTHER
AND WE HIT IT OFF,
WE'RE, LIKE, "OH, MY GOD,
WE NEED TO LIVE TOGETHER."
CAN WE PLEASE HAVE
THESE THERAPY SESSIONS?
- YEAH.
- AT LEAST ONCE A WEEK.
'CAUSE THAT'S
WHAT BEST FRIENDS DO.
I'M [bleep] UP.
- [chuckling]
WE'RE MOVING TO THE CITY
FOR ONE LAST HURRAH.
WHY ARE YOU SO CREEPY?
- SORRY, NEIGHBORS, 'CAUSE
THESE BITCHES ARE MOVING IN.
[both scream]
- [laughing]
- JENNI!
- EAT IT!
- NO.
[overlapping
screams and shouts]
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT, I LOVE IT *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
[electronic music]
* *
- NICOLE AND I,
WE'RE MOVING IN TOGETHER
'CAUSE I'M
ABOUT TO HIT 30
IN A COUPLE YEARS,
AND THAT'S IT.
I AM INTERESTED
IN THE TWO-BEDROOM
YOU HAVE AVAILABLE
ON YOUR WEBSITE.
30 IS MY LIMIT,
SO I HAVE THREE YEARS
FOR LIKE A BUCKET LIST
TO GET EVERYTHING DONE.
- SO YOU WANT THE ONE-BEDROOM
OR THE TWO-BEDROOM?
OR WE HAVE
A THREE-BEDROOM.
- I WOULD PREFER
A TWO-BEDROOM.
IT'S GONNA BE FOR ME
AND MY GIRLFRIEND.
- OH, YEAH, WE DON'T HAVE
A TWO-BEDROOM.
- WHAT DO YOU HAVE AGAIN?
- WE HAVE A ONE-BEDROOM
AND A TWO-BEDROOM
AND A THREE-BEDROOM.
- [laughing]
- NOT THE TWO-BEDROOM.
- WE'RE NOT TRYING
TO TAKE A [bleep]-HOLE.
WE WANT TO LIVE THERE.
IT AIN'T EASY FINDING A PLACE
IN THE CITY.
- UM, THERE'S DEFINITELY
SOME PROPERTIES
THAT WE CAN SHOW YOU.
- DO YOU GUYS TAKE DOGS?
- DO THEY BARK A LOT?
- NO, NOT AT ALL.
- OKAY, UM...
[barking]
- SHH!
- HOLD ON. 9:00 A.M. TOMORROW.
DOES 9:00 A.M. WORK FOR YOU?
- YEAH.
- OKAY.
- BYE NOW.
[pop music]
* *
- NICOLE, NICOLE.
- MOM, GO AWAY!
- RIGHT.
- [grunting]
I DEFINITELY DON'T WANT TO BE
ONE OF THOSE KIDS
THAT ARE, LIKE,
40 YEARS OLD,
THEY STILL LIVE
WITH THEIR PARENTS,
AND I FEEL
LIKE BEING 24, LIKE,
I'M ALMOST AT THAT POINT
WHERE I'M GONNA BE
ONE OF THOSE PEOPLE,
SO WE NEED TO CUT
THE UMBILICAL CORD
AND I NEED TO GO
AND LIVE ON MY OWN.
- MORNING.
UM, I KIND OF WANT TO GET
MY OWN PLACE WITH JENNI.
- REALLY?
- YEAH.
- LIKE, NO OFFENSE,
BUT I'M 24 AND I'M STILL
LIVING HERE.
ALL MY FRIENDS ARE MOVED OUT
IN THEIR OWN APARTMENTS,
AND, YOU KNOW, I KIND OF WANT
TO BE ON MY OWN WITH JENNI.
- AND WHERE WOULD YOU FIND
A PLACE TO LIVE?
- JERSEY.
- OF COURSE.
- WELL, SOMEWHERE
IN JERSEY OBVIOUSLY.
- SOMEWHERE IN JERSEY?
WHO'S GONNA DO ALL THE SHOPPING
AND THE LAUNDRY?
THAT'S NOT YOUR STYLE.
- OKAY, YOU'RE ANNOYING.
YOU'RE, LIKE, THE BUZZ KILL
TO THIS NEWS
RIGHT NOW.
- IT'S NOT YOUR FORTE.
- OKAY, WELL,
I WENT GROCERY SHOPPING BEFORE.
- YEAH?
- THAT'S FUN.
- YOU GONNA SPLIT THE FOOD BILL
DOWN THE MIDDLE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT'S THE WORD--
- YOU GONNA BUY YOUR OWN--
- IT'S--IS "KOSHER" THE RIGHT--
THE RIGHT WORD
FOR JENNI?
- I DO KNOW THAT THAT'S THE FOOD
THAT JEWISH PEOPLE EAT.
- [laughing]
NO, JENNI--JENNI'S NOT--
- JENNI'S NOT JEWISH.
[laughing]
- WHOOPS.
- SEE, I THINK KOSHER FOOD
IS, LIKE, ORGANIC, HEALTHY FOOD.
BUT JEWISH PEOPLE
EAT ORGANIC FOOD TOO.
SO I FEEL LIKE
IT'S ALL IN THE SAME.
- SO YOU TOLD
JENNI EVERYTHING
BEFORE YOU DECIDE
TO MOVE IN, AND...
- I DIDN'T REALLY
TELL JENNI YET.
- OH.
- BUT I'LL TELL HER
WHEN I SEE HER.
- SHE'LL BE OKAY,
AND YOU'LL TALK IT OUT
BEFORE YOU MAKE
THIS COMMITMENT?
- SHE'S MY BEST FRIEND,
AND, YOU KNOW, SHE GETS IT.
I'M NERVOUS ABOUT
TELLING JENNI MY SECRET,
JUST BECAUSE I'M SCARED
THAT SHE'S GONNA
CALL OFF ME AND HER
LIVING TOGETHER.
AND I'M JUST GONNA BE, LIKE,
"NO, BITCH."
"LET'S JUST [bleep] DO THIS
BECAUSE I NEED IT."
THANKS, MOM, FOR THE ADVICE.
- ANYTIME. I LOVE YOU.
LOVE YOU A LOT.
- DON'T CRY.
- OKAY, I WON'T.
- EW, YOU ARE!
[hip-hop music]
* *
- HI, PRETTY LADY.
- I AM VERY SCARED
AND CONCERNED
THAT ROGER MAY NOT TAKE
THIS WHOLE MOVE POSITIVE,
BUT I HOPE
HE'S READY FOR IT.
- I WANT
TO BE SUPPORTIVE.
I DON'T KNOW
THAT IT'S A GREAT IDEA,
I GOT TO BE HONEST WITH YOU.
I MEAN...
NICOLE'S A HANDFUL,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
AND--AND YOU KNOW
I LOVE NICOLE.
AND YOU THINK THAT'S
A GOOD IDEA HONESTLY?
- YES AND NO.
- THINK THAT'S GONNA
HELP OUR RELATIONSHIP?
DO YOU THINK THAT'S GONNA HELP
YOUR AND NICOLE'S RELATIONSHIP?
- YES, BUT, YOU KNOW,
DO WHAT WE GOTTA DO.
- DEFINE "DO WHAT
WE GOTTA DO."
THAT COULD MEAN GANGBANGS,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
WHAT IS "DO WHAT
WE GOTTA DO"?
- NO, NOTHING,
I'M NOT TRYING--
IT'S, LIKE,
COMING OFF BAD.
- IS THE SIMPLEST WAY
TO PUT THIS
THAT YOU JUST WANT
ONE LAST HURRAH OR SOMETHING?
- NOT A GANGBANG HURRAH,
JUST, LIKE, ONE LAST--
I JUST DON'T WANT TO BE LIKE
THAT GIRL AT 45 YEARS OLD
BEING, LIKE, "DAMN, I WISH I--
I LIVED BY THE CITY
WITH MY GIRLFRIEND."
- IS THIS REALLY WHAT YOU
WANT TO DO? HONESTLY?
- YEAH, BECAUSE I DON'T WANT
ANY REGRETS IN LIFE.
- IT'S GONNA BE CRAZY.
- IT'S NOT GONNA BE CRAZY.
- HOW CAN IT NOT BE CRAZY?
YOU COULDN'T LIVE IN ANTARCTICA
IN A [bleep] IGLOO WITH NICOLE
AND NOT BE CRAZY.
- ROGER'S BEING A LITTLE
SKEPTICAL RIGHT NOW.
BUT I GET IT.
HE KNOWS NICOLE.
SHE DOESN'T CLEAN.
SHE DOESN'T MAKE HER BED.
SHE DOESN'T DO LAUNDRY.
SHE DOESN'T COOK.
SHE DOESN'T CLEAN AGAIN.
SHE LIKES TO GET DRUNK.
SHE LIKES TO GET WASTED.
SHE LIKES TO HAVE A GOOD TIME.
SHE LIKES TO GET DRUNK.
SHE LIKES TO GET WASTED.
- BUT I'M OKAY WITH IT.
- I'LL HAVE A GOOD TIME.
AND THEN YOU HAVE
A GOOD TIME.
- OH, I'LL BE HAVING
- IF ROGER DOES ANYTHING
WHEN I'M GONE,
HIS [bleep] WILL
BE ABOVE MY FIREPLACE.
LIKE, LET'S GET REAL.
- THERE'S GONNA BE THE WORLD'S
BIGGEST STRIPPER POLE IN THERE.
JUST SAYING.
- [clicks tongue]
- STRIPPERS NEED LOVE TOO.
- WORST CASE--
AS FAST AS I MOVE IN
IS AS FAST
AS I MOVE OUT.
- I GUESS. THAT'S ONE WAY
TO LOOK AT IT.
- I HAVE SOMETHING
TO TELL YOU
THAT, UM, I REALLY WANTED
TO TELL YOU FOR, LIKE, A WHILE.
I'M PREGNANT.
AND ENGAGED.
- NICOLE?
- CRICKETS.
OH, MY GOD,
EVERY TIME MY DAD WALKS IN
WITH THAT STUPID
BLACK FILING CABINET,
I'M JUST, LIKE, THIS ISN'T
GONNA BE A FUN CONVERSATION.
I'M, LIKE, "GO AWAY."
- THIS ISN'T GONNA BE
A SUMMER HOUSE
LIKE YOU GUYS DID
AT THE JERSEY SHORE.
THIS IS GONNA BE
YOUR PLACE TO LIVE.
- THANK YOU, CAPTAIN OBVIOUS,
I KNOW.
- I GUESS THERE'S SOME THINGS
WE OUGHTA PROBABLY GO THROUGH.
- WHAT ARE YOU EVEN
TAKING OUT RIGHT NOW?
- WELL, I WANTED TO SHOW YOU
SOME OF THE STUFF--
- YOU HAVE YOUR FILES?
- YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO SET THIS STUFF UP.
THIS IS ALL STUFF THAT YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE TO TAKE CARE OF.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE RENT,
INSURANCE, GAS, ELECTRIC.
- SAY WE DON'T PUT
ANY LIGHT BULBS ON...
AND WE USE CANDLES.
SEE, IT WOULD ACTUALLY
SAVE A LOT OF MONEY,
IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
I MEAN, I KNOW A LOT
OF AMISH PEOPLE DO IT.
THEY DON'T USE ELECTRICITY.
AND THEY'RE RICH, I FEEL.
THEY HAVE THEIR OWN
FREAKING COMPANIES.
LIKE, EVERYWHERE.
- THE SEWER BILL.
- YOU HAVE TO PAY
FOR TAKING A [bleep]?
- GO DO YOUR LOOKING,
BUT DON'T GO
SIGNING ANYTHING,
AND LET ME
LOOK AT IT FIRST.
DON'T SIGN NOTHING.
ZERO.
- WELL, YOU MAKE IT SEEM
REALLY HARD.
IF YOU CAN DO IT,
I'M SURE A MONKEY CAN DO IT.
- OH, GEE, THANK YOU.
- [giggling]
- THANK YOU. THAT'S WHY YOU GOT
WHAT YOU GOT, RIGHT?
- WE'LL SEE.
- YEAH, WE WILL SEE.
OH, GOD.
[computer beeping]
- OOPS.
- GOOD GIRL.
- HI!
ME AND JENNI ARE BOTH READY
TO FIND AN APARTMENT.
SO, YOU KNOW, THE FACT
THAT WE'RE BOTH READY
TO MAKE THIS COMMITMENT,
IT'S REALLY EXCITING.
WHAT'S UP, POOP?
- NOTHING. WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- NOTHING.
THINKING ABOUT YOU.
- AWW. I'M LOVING THE BOW.
- YOU LOOK PALE.
- [bleep] ME.
- WELL, I LOOK CUTE.
- AND IT'S BEGUN.
GUESS WHAT?
- WHAT?
- I TALKED
TO REALTORS TODAY.
- REALLY?
- YEAH.
I THINK WE SHOULD GO LOOK
FOR APARTMENTS TOMORROW.
I GAVE THEM, LIKE,
A GENERIC...
ALLOWS ANIMALS,
TWO-BEDROOM--
- YOU'RE BRINGING
YOUR DOGS?
- I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
I JUST SAID "ALLOWING ANIMALS."
- I GUESS.
THE ONLY THING
I'M WORRIED ABOUT
IS THEY POOP AND PEE
EVERYWHERE,
SO AS LONG AS THEY DON'T
DO THAT ON MY THINGS,
I THINK WE'LL BE FINE.
- HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT GOING
IN THE CITY
AT 9:00 IN THE MORNING?
- WAIT, WHAT?
- DUDE, THIS GUY
STARTS EARLY.
- IF YOU BRING ME A BAGEL,
I GUESS I'LL COME.
- [laughing]
I'LL BRING YOU A BAGEL.
- ALL RIGHT, WELL...
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU, BYE.
MOMMY'S AS WHITE AS YOU.
[hip-hop music]
* *
- [shivering] CHILLY.
I [bleep] LOOK PALE.
BAGEL, BAGEL, BAGEL.
* *
GPS voice: THE ROUTE
GUIDANCE WILL START NOW.
NEXT, SHARP RIGHT.
THEN RIGHT TURN.
- [bleep], THIS IS IT.
SEE, I CAN'T DO THIS.
[bleep], ONE WAY [bleep].
OH, A SPEED BUMP.
OKAY...
"DO NOT ENTER"?
WHICH WAY DO I GO?
- MM...
THIS IS BEAUTIFUL.
[knocking,
shaking door knob]
- GOD, I ALMOST HIT
THAT CAR.
- AM I THE ONLY ONE
ON TIME?
IS THIS SERIOUSLY HAPPENING
RIGHT NOW?
OBVIOUSLY NOBODY'S
ON TIME. FIGURES.
OH...IT'S SO COLD.
[phone ringing]
- STOP CALLING ME.
LIKE, I'M ALMOST THERE.
IT'S CALLED TRAFFIC,
AND IT'S CALLED THE CITY.
[phone ringing]
- THIS IS A REALLY [bleep]
START TO HOUSE HUNTING,
BECAUSE I'M LITERALLY, LIKE,
ON THE STAIRS
OF THE FIRST LOCATION
LIKE A HOMELESS PERSON.
I HAVE TO PEE,
I'M FREEZING,
AND I FEEL LIKE
IT'S ABOUT TO RAIN.
[phone ringing]
- HI, YOU'VE REACHED
THE VOICEMAIL OF--
- OKAY, DOUCHEBAG.
- OH, MY GOD.
NOW I'M LOST.
- OH, MY GOD, I'M GONNA [bleep]
PUNCH NICOLE IN THE FACE.
AND THEN I'M GONNA PUNCH
THE REALTOR.
- IS THAT
THE EMPIRE STATE BUILDING?
- I DON'T LIKE
ANYBODY ANYMORE.
THERE SHE [bleep] IS.
IN HER RIDICULOUSLY
GHETTO TRUCK.
[horn honking]
- NICOLE SHOWS UP FIRST.
I'M KIND OF IMPRESSED,
'CAUSE I REALLY THOUGHT
THE REALTOR WOULD'VE BEEN FIRST.
CAN I GET IN YOUR TRUCK
'CAUSE I'M [bleep] FREEZING?
'CAUSE YOU
TOOK FOREVER?
- WHY, IS HE NOT HERE?
- NO, NOBODY'S HERE.
OH...I LOVE YOU.
- WHERE'S YOUR CAR?
- IT'S BACK THERE.
- SO I HAVE TO PARALLEL?
- YEAH, I WANT TO SEE THIS.
- I NEVER REALLY
PARALLEL PARKED BEFORE,
SO I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT THE [bleep] I'M DOING.
OH, MY GOD,
THIS IS SO EMBARRASSING.
- ALL RIGHT BRING IT BACK.
CRANK YOUR WHEEL.
YEAH, CUT IT.
I HAVE TO TEACH NICOLE RIGHT NOW
HOW TO PARALLEL PARK.
I DON'T KNOW HOW SHE'S
GONNA LAST IN THIS CITY
WITH THIS MONSTER TRUCK.
DO NOT TOUCH THE WHEEL.
- OH, DON'T TOUCH IT?
- NO, LIKE, KEEP IT--
ALL RIGHT, STOP.
STOP! STOP,
STOP, STOP, STOP.
OKAY, GO STRAIGHT.
BUT CRANK IT ALL THE WAY.
STOP.
- I'M SECOND-GUESSING
MY TRUCK DECISION NOW.
ALL RIGHT, I'M CURVING IT.
- STOP...STOP!
OH, MY GOD!
OKAY.
- IF I KNEW I WAS MOVING
TO THE CITY BEFORE,
I WOULD'VE NEVER
GOT THE TRUCK.
SO...I'M SCREWED.
- I HAVE TO RUN.
- WHY?
- I HAVE TO GO
TO THE BATHROOM.
- YOU'RE GONNA GO OUT
IN THE WILDERNESS?
- I HAVE TO PEE.
I CAN'T HOLD IT AT THIS POINT.
HOMEBOY IS NOT MAKING A GOOD
FIRST IMPRESSION RIGHT NOW.
NOT AT ALL.
- JUST PEE OUT HERE.
- DO I CHANGE
A TAMPON DOWN THERE?
[laughter]
THERE'S AN ISSUE.
- CAN'T YOU WAIT,
LIKE, FIVE MINUTES?
- I'VE WAITED 30--
- IS THIS VICTOR?
VICTOR?
- YES.
- DUDE, WHAT THE [bleep]?
- I'M SORRY.
I WAS TRYING TO FIND
A PARKING SPOT,
AND I WAS ON MY WAY HERE.
- IT'S ALL GOOD.
- I JUST HAVE TO USE
THE BATHROOM.
- OKAY, COME ON IN.
- NICE SUIT.
- THANK YOU.
- VICTOR THE REALTOR
IS CUTE,
BUT HIS BLAZER
MAKES MY EYEBALLS BLEED.
WHAT VINTAGE SHOP FROM THE 80s
DID YOU PICK THAT UP AT?
- COME ON IN. YOU CAN USE
THE BATHROOM, I GUESS,
BEFORE I DO
THE SHOWING.
- OKAY. YOU START LOOKING.
- OKAY.
- THIS IS THE FRONT BEDROOM
ON THE STREET,
AND THEN WE HAVE ANOTHER ONE.
- YO, THERE'S NO TOILET PAPER!
- DO YOU HAVE
TOILET PAPER FOR HER?
- UM...
THERE MIGHT BE
TOILET PAPER UPSTAIRS.
IF YOU LIKE, I CAN GO
TAKE A LOOK FOR YOU.
- OH, MY GOD.
- SHE HAS HER PERIOD.
- OH, BOO,
YOUR BAGEL BAG!
YOUR BAGEL BAG
HAS PAPER!
- CAN YOU NOT WIPE YOUR VAGINA
WITH MY BAGEL?
- THANK GOD I BOUGHT YOU
THAT BAGEL.
- WHAT IF THE TOILET
WASN'T WORKING
BECAUSE NO ONE
LIVES THERE?
- WELL, MY TAMPON WOULD
BE HANGING OUT THERE RIGHT NOW.
- THAT'S DISGUSTING.
- YOU'VE DONE WORSE.
- YEAH, THAT'S TRUE.
- THIS IS A GOOD AREA?
- YES.
THIS IS WHERE--
A LOT OF FAMILIES
AND COUPLES HAVE BEEN
MOVING HERE.
- I DON'T WANT TO LIVE NEXT
TO FAMILIES AND COUPLES...
- BUT YOU WANT IT
TO BE SAFE.
- WHAT PART OF JERSEY CITY
DO YOU LIVE IN?
- UM, I LIVE
IN THE GREENVILLE SECTION.
- I WANT TO GO
TO THE GREENVILLE SECTION.
- I'M ELENA.
- THIS IS ELENA, GUYS.
- HI, NICOLE.
- HI, HOW ARE YOU?
- IS THIS PARKING
BACK HERE?
- IT'S NOT FOR THIS BUILDING.
- SO YOU HAVE TO PARALLEL.
- YOU HAVE TO PARK
IN THE STREET.
- SO PRETTY.
MAKES ME FEEL
LIKE I'M HOME IN SEASIDE.
MOVE ON.
- NEXT ONE.
THIS REMINDS ME OF,
LIKE, MY MOM'S HOUSE.
- AAH!
OH, MY GOD. COOL!
- THERE'S A ROACH IN THERE.
- MOVING ON.
- AS I MENTIONED,
THIS HAS ALL BEEN RENOVATED.
IT'S A RAILROAD-STYLE
APARTMENT.
BASICALLY MEANS YOU HAVE TO
WALK THROUGH ONE BEDROOM
TO GET TO THE NEXT.
- I THOUGHT IT WAS BUILT
IN THE RAILROAD AGES
WHEN YOU'RE THINKING OF PEOPLE
BUILDING RAILROADS, SO...
HOW OLD
IS THIS BUILDING?
- PROBABLY BUILT
IN THE EARLY 1900s.
- OH, [bleep] THAT.
AAH!
THERE COULD'VE BEEN MURDERS
HERE YOU DON'T KNOW ABOUT,
HOMICIDES...THAT'S, LIKE,
THE SAME THING, RIGHT?
DOES IT ECHO IN HERE?
HELLO!
YEAH, SO I CAN
HEAR YOU HAVE SEX.
- THE--I COULD--NO.
THIS IS--IT'S--NO.
DO YOU GUYS [bleep]?
- NO.
- YOU REALLY DON'T?
- AWW.
- ANYWAY, SO...
- JUST TRYING TO BREAK THE ICE.
JUST TRYING TO BREAK
THE ICE.
VICTOR AND ELENA CLAIM
THAT THEY DON'T HAVE SEX.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
- THEY'RE TWO
GOOD LOOKING PEOPLE
AND THEY'RE IN
THE SAME BUSINESS,
AND SOMETIMES PEOPLE
MIX BUSINESS WITH PLEASURE.
- THAT'S WHY ROGER WORKS
WITH TRUCK DRIVERS.
- 'CAUSE HE [bleep] THEM?
- NO.
SO HE DOESN'T HAVE TO LOOK
AT HOT GIRLS ALL DAY, [bleep].
- [chuckling]
MOVING ON.
- MOVING ON.
- EW! OH, MY GOD,
HE LOOKS LIKE A PEDOPHILE.
EW.
both: EW!
- WHY ARE YOU
SO CREEPY?
- OH, GOD, JENNI,
OH, MY GOD.
- [laughing]
- EW, EW, EW,
EW, EW.
HE'S SCARY.
both: AAH!
- GOOD-BYE.
- SO FAR, HOUSE HUNTING
IS KIND OF A LITTLE STRESSFUL
BECAUSE WE REALLY HAVEN'T
FOUND ANYTHING PERFECT YET.
SO IT'S, LIKE,
ARE WE GOING TO?
- OH.
IS THIS IT?
- IS THIS A GARAGE?
I'M THINKING THIS IS EITHER,
LIKE, AN OLD WAREHOUSE,
OR A FRICKIN' FIREHOUSE.
EITHER ONE, I MEAN,
THAT'S KIND OF WEIRD.
LIKE, WHO LIVES
IN A FIREHOUSE?
- OH, MY GOD.
- I'M NOT LIKING
THESE [bleep] STAIRS.
THIS REMINDS ME
OF [bleep] ITALY.
I DON'T FEEL LIKE WALKING
UP THESE STAIRS ALL THE TIME.
HOLY [bleep].
THIS IS HUGE!
- I DIDN'T EXPECT THIS.
- WELL, YOU GUYS WANT TO START
FROM THE BEDROOMS FIRST?
- SURE.
- WORK YOUR WAYS BACK.
- IT'S GOT BIG BED.
IT'S A NORMAL BED.
[laughing] DO WE GET
TO KEEP THE BED?
- OH, IT SMELLS
LIKE GRANDMA'S.
- THERE'S TWO LEVELS
LIKE A LOFT.
PUT 'EM UPSTAIRS.
- JUST LIKE HER STAIRS?
- YEAH.
- OH, MY GOD,
I'M LOVING THIS.
- THIS BETTER [bleep]
TAKE DOGS.
- I MADE SURE OF IT.
THEY DEFINITELY TAKE DOGS HERE.
SO WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK
OF THE OPEN FEELING, THOUGH?
- I HONESTLY DON'T THINK
ANYTHING COMPARES TO THIS
BECAUSE IT'S JUST
SO BIG.
- I LOVE THIS PLACE.
WE'RE JUST--
- THIS IS DEFINITELY
A BACHELORETTE PAD.
- SO DO YOU WANT ME
TO LEAVE YOU ALONE SO YOU GUYS
CAN DISCUSS IT AND THEN SEE
WHAT YOU GUYS THINK?
- SURE.
IT'S A LITTLE PRESSURE
JUST BECAUSE WE REALLY WANT
TO FIND A HOUSE TODAY.
SO IT'S KIND OF LIKE
WE NEED TO DO THIS NOW,
MAKE A DECISION.
SO?
- THIS, TO ME, IS FIVE-STAR.
- THIS IS DEFINITELY
FIVE-STAR.
- YEAH, I LOVE
THE OPENNESS.
LIKE, OUR BEDROOMS ARE
IDENTICAL, AND IT'S SO CUTE.
- I'M KIND OF GLAD
IT'S EQUAL.
AND I'M THE CHIEF,
AND YOU'RE THE CAPTAIN.
WE WANT THIS PLACE.
- I'M READY.
YOU?
- WELL, UM...
I HAVE SOMETHING
TO TELL YOU
THAT, UM, I REALLY WANTED
TO TELL YOU FOR, LIKE, A WHILE,
BUT I JUST WANTED TO WAIT.
- I DON'T LIKE THAT,
'CAUSE ANYTHING COULD COME OUT
OF THAT GIRL'S MOUTH.
ANYTHING.
YEAH?
- UM...
I'M NERVOUS ABOUT
TELLING JENNI MY SECRET
JUST BECAUSE I JUST
DON'T WANT HER TO BE UPSET
AND BE, LIKE,
"WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?"
SO BEFORE WE GET ALL SERIOUS
AND SIGN THE LEASE
AND ALL THIS STUFF,
I REALLY NEED
TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE MY BEST FRIEND.
UM...
SO JIONNI PROPOSED,
AND I'M ENGAGED.
- NO, YOU'RE NOT.
- YEAH, I AM.
- I SWEAR.
LIKE, I'M ENGAGED.
- YOU WOULD'VE TOLD ME.
- THERE'S MORE
SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW ON THE WAY,
AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
UM...
SO JIONNI PROPOSED,
AND I'M ENGAGED.
- NO, YOU'RE NOT.
- YEAH, I AM.
- I SWEAR.
LIKE, I'M ENGAGED.
- YOU WOULD'VE TOLD ME.
- I DIDN'T WANT TO TELL YOU
BECAUSE THEN I DIDN'T WANT YOU
TO NOT WANT
TO MOVE IN WITH ME.
- YOU WAITED?
- YEAH, BECAUSE I-I WANT THIS
MOMENT TO DEFINITELY HAPPEN.
- I FEEL LIKE I'M IN
THE TWILIGHT ZONE RIGHT NOW,
BECAUSE I HONESTLY THOUGHT
THAT I WOULD BE THE ONE ENGAGED
BEFORE ANYONE ELSE.
THAT'S NOT REAL.
- OKAY.
YEAH, SO...
- IT'S BIG.
- IT'S HUGE.
- I AM, LIKE, DUMBFOUNDED.
I...PFFT.
SO WHAT THE [bleep]--UH, NO,
WELL, CONGRATULATIONS.
HOLD ON, NO, NO, NO.
- THANK YOU.
- WHAT THE [bleep]
DOES HE SAY ABOUT THIS?
- WELL, OBVIOUSLY, WE'RE NOT
GONNA GET MARRIED, LIKE, SOON.
WE'RE GONNA WAIT,
YOU KNOW?
WE'RE GONNA BE ENGAGED
FOR A COUPLE YEARS.
- I GOT THE CHILLS,
AND I'M, LIKE, REALLY EXCITED,
BUT I'M LIKE, OH, MY GOD,
WE'RE TRYING
TO GET AN APARTMENT, BUT YOU'RE
ENGAGED TO SOMEONE, LIKE...
SO MANY EMOTIONS
ARE GOING AROUND
THAT I'M, LIKE, SPEECHLESS.
YOU'RE SURE YOU WANT
TO DO THIS?
BE ENGAGED?
I THOUGHT I WAS GONNA BE
THE FIRST ONE GETTING ENGAGED.
- YEAH, WELL, HE ASKED.
- HE JUST WANTED TO?
- HE KIND OF HAD A REASON.
UM, AND IT'S DEFINITELY
GONNA CHANGE YOUR LIFE
ALONG WITH MINE.
- HUH?
- SO HE PRETTY MUCH ASKED ME
TO GET MARRIED--
AND ALSO BECAUSE HE, YOU KNOW,
WE WANT TO GET MARRIED--
IS BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT.
- WHAT DO I SAY?
- I'M PREGNANT.
AND ENGAGED.
INSTEAD OF LIFE THROWING ME
A CURVEBALL,
IT THREW ME A SPERM BALL.
OBVIOUSLY.
SO LET'S GO SIGN
THIS LEASE.
- AAH! [bleep]!
OKAY, I'M GOOD.
I AM MOVING IN...
WE'LL SURVIVE THIS.
WITH A PREGNANT,
ENGAGED SNOOKI.
IT'S MOVING!
- OH, I GOTTA THROW UP.
HONESTLY, I REALLY DIDN'T KNOW
THAT I COULD MAKE A BABY.
SO THE FACT THAT I CAN
REPRODUCE IS VERY SCARY.
- I'M VERY HAPPY FOR YOU.
- WHAT'S THE OVER-UNDER
ON HIM BEING
FIVE-FOOT?
[laughter]
- NICOLE!
- ME AND JENNI, OBVIOUSLY
WE'RE GONNA CLASH A LITTLE BIT.
STOP SCREAMING AT ME.
YOU BE CONSIDERATE.
I'M PREGNANT
AND WE'RE ALL...WHOO!
- THIS IS SUPPOSED TO BE
ME AND NICOLE'S LAST HURRAH,
AND SHE'S NOT HURRAH-ING.
- I DON'T THINK I WANT
TO LIVE WITH JENNI ANYMORE.
- THE ONLY THING YOU'RE
WINNING AT, ROGER, IS LOSING ME.
IF THIS IS GONNA BE
WHAT WE HAVE,
I NEED SOMETHING ELSE.
[sobbing]
- CAN I HUG YOU?
ME AND JENNI BICKER
LIKE WE'RE [bleep] SISTERS,
BUT, LIKE,
I WOULD DIE FOR YOU.
- YEAH, 100%, I WOULD TAKE
A BULLET FOR YOU.
- MM-HMM. BUT LET'S MAKE SURE
THAT DOESN'T HAPPEN.
- YEAH.
OH, MY GOD! WHAT DID YOU DO
TO [bleep] BARNEY?
both: AWW!
- DID IT [bleep] ON ME?
- HEY!
- OH!
- [laughing]
- I THINK RIGHT NOW
IS THE PRIME TIME FOR US
TO BE TOGETHER,
YOU KNOW, TO JUST ENJOY LIFE
AS BEST FRIENDS.
both: MWAH!
- * HERE WE GO AGAIN *