- YOUR LITTLE BABY.
- YOU CREATED THAT...
DRUNK NIGHT.
- NO.
- I THINK WE SHOULD INVITE
THE ROOMMATES OVER.
I DO HAVE IMPORTANT NEWS
TO TELL THEM.
- OH, YOU WANT TO TELL THEM?
- I THINK
I SHOULD TELL THEM.
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT, I LOVE IT *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
[drum music]
- THE REAL REASON WHY I INVITED
YOU GUYS HERE...
- UH-OH.
- IS BECAUSE ME
AND JIONNI ARE ENGAGED.
- WHAT?
- OH!
- WAIT A SECOND.
TIME OUT.
I'M A LITTLE UPSET
ABOUT THIS.
EVERYBODY KNOWS YOU DON'T EVEN
GET A GIRLFRIEND
FROM THE JERSEY SHORE.
A WIFE? A HUSBAND?
THAT'S OUT OF CONTROL.
YOU THINK TWO YEARS
IS A LONG ENOUGH TIME
TO MARRY SOMEBODY...
- OH, HERE WE GO.
- TO SPEND
THE REST OF YOUR DAYS WITH?
- LIKE, YEAH.
- YOU KNOW THAT'S ONE PERSON
FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE,
RIGHT?
- YOU KNOW THAT'S ONE PENIS
FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE,
RIGHT?
- I LOVE HIS PENIS.
- VINNY, YOU'RE, LIKE, HATING
ON THE WHOLE ENGAGEMENT?
- I'M TOTALLY JEALOUS,
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH.
- CAN I SEE THE RING?
- WOW, THAT'S AMAZING.
JIONNI CAN'T AFFORD
THAT [bleep].
THE KID DOESN'T HAVE NO JOB.
- DID SHE BUY IT?
- [laughs] STOP.
[laughter]
- THIS IS NOT SOMETHING
TO BUST MY BALLS ABOUT.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
BE HAPPY FOR ME.
- YOU GUYS ARE GONNA BE DIVORCED
SOON ANYWAY.
- GREAT.
- OH, BOY.
- AWKWARD.
[laughs]
- WELL, CONGRATULATIONS
ON THE ENGAGEMENT.
- YEAH. DIG IN.
[bleep].
- ARE YOU ENGAGED TOO?
- NO. I WISH.
- GIRL, YOU'RE
GETTING UP THERE, GIRL.
YOU NEED TO GET ON THAT.
- I KNOW.
ASK ROGER.
- HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN
WITH ROG?
- ALMOST TWO YEARS.
- HOW LONG HAVE YOU
BEEN WITH JIONNI?
- LIKE, THREE MONTHS.
- NO.
[laughter]
ALMOST TWO YEARS.
- THAT'S CRAZY YOU'RE ENGAGED.
THAT'S CRAZY.
YOU GREW UP.
I CAN'T PICTURE SNOOKI
BEING TIED DOWN,
UNLESS IT'S TO, LIKE,
A BEDPOST OR SOMETHING.
- WE'RE GONNA START LOADING
THE DISHWASHER.
- THIS IS WHAT
YOU COULD HAVE HAD, BABY.
[laughter]
I CLEAN AND I WORK.
- [laughs]
- SO DOES JIONNI.
- WHERE?
- ON YOUR VAGINA.
- SO?
[laughter]
- JUST PUT EVERYTHING
ON THE COUNTER.
WE'LL WORRY ABOUT IT LATER.
- IT'S TIME FOR DESSERT,
AND HONESTLY,
I'M NOT EVEN EXCITED TO TELL
THE ROOMMATES I'M PREGNANT
BECAUSE OF THE REACTION
I GOT SAYING I'M ENGAGED.
JENNI, CAN YOU HELP ME?
- YEAH.
- IT'S MY CAKE.
WAIT FOR IT.
- OH, I GOTTA GET A KNIFE.
IT IS DESSERT TIME,
AND NICOLE LOOKS LIKE
A BAG OF
[bleep] SHAKING BONES
[laughter]
- SOMETHING'S GOING ON
WITH THIS CAKE.
- I'VE NEVER SEEN NICOLE
THIS TYPE OF NERVOUS.
- IT LOOKS LIKE YOUR BOW.
- READY?
- THAT'S CUTE.
- IT'S MY CAKE.
I LOVE IT.
BUT YOU HAVE TO SEE THE TOP
THAT'S ON IT.
- IT LOOKS LIKE YOU
RIGHT NOW.
- WOW, THAT IS CRAZY.
- WHAT DOES IT SAY?
- "BY THE WAY,
I'M PREGNANT."
- HOLY [bleep], WHAT?
- OH, MY GOD.
- YOU'RE PREGNANT?
- HOLD ON ONE SECOND.
YOU'RE KNOCKED UP?
- YEAH.
- WOW.
- OH!
OH, WHAT'S COMING OUT
OF THE BOOB?
- WHAT ELSE ARE YOU HIDING?
- AT FIRST, HE WAS LIKE,
OH, MY GOD.
- OH, MY GOD,
IT LOOKS JUST LIKE ME.
- VINNY.
- I DID NOT HAVE SEX
WITH SNOOKI,
LIKE, FOUR MONTHS AGO...
I DON'T THINK.
- I THOUGHT YOU PULLED OUT!
- HIS COUCH PULLS OUT.
- OH, [bleep]!
- IT'S NOT YOURS!
- YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
- YO, DNA TEST, BRO.
- OH, MY GOD, IT LOOKS LIKE
A LITTLE MEATBALL.
- YES!
- MY MEATBALL'S ENGAGED,
AND SHE'S FRICKING GETTING
PREGNANT OVER HERE.
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON?
RIGHT NOW, I FEEL LIKE
THE ONLY MEATBALL I HAVE LEFT
IS THE ONE ON MY PLATE.
NO MORE MEATBALL DAYS,
UNTIL...
- WHEN IT POPS OUT,
THEN I'LL--
- WHEN IT POPS OUT, THEN YOU
GOTTA TAKE CARE OF IT.
- TAKE CARE OF IT?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- I KNOW.
- IT'S NOT JUST A PREGNANCY.
- I KNOW, BUT I'M ALLOWED TO
GO OUT ONCE TONIGHT.
- YAY! I DID IT! WHOO!
- IT'S NOT A RACE.
WHEN YOU CROSS THE LINE,
IT'S NOT LIKE, "I WIN!"
- JENNI, YOU KNOW THIS,
AND WE'RE TALKING ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE SO ANNOYING.
- OH, FIRST FIGHT!
FIRST FIGHT!
- FIRST HOME FIGHT!
- FIRST FIGHT!
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- STOP BEING SAD.
- LIKE, THIS IS SUPPOSED TO BE,
LIKE, A FUN MOMENT FOR ME,
AND HONESTLY,
AS A BEST FRIEND,
JENNI IS SUCKING
AT SUPPORTING ME.
- I THOUGHT IT WAS
GONNA BE YOU FIRST.
- I THOUGHT
YOU WANTED A KID SOON.
- NOT AFTER THE [bleep] I'VE
BEEN GOING THROUGH WITH HER.
SHE'S MISERABLE.
[laughs]
BECAUSE OF HER, I AM PETRIFIED
TO HAVE A KID.
- THAT'S REAL NICE.
WHY DON'T YOU MAKE HER FEEL
A LITTLE BETTER?
- [laughs]
TELL HER HOW YOU REALLY FEEL.
[laughs]
- THIS WASN'T HOW I WANTED
DINNER.
[laughter]
- IT SUCKS.
- IT NEVER IS, SNOOKS.
- SO DYSFUNCTIONAL.
- YOU'RE GONNA BE
A NICE YOUNG MOM WITH YOUR KID,
AND YOU'RE GONNA
GROW UP AND HAVE, LIKE,
A NICE, LIKE, LIFE
WITH YOUR KID.
- IT'S GONNA BE
THE MOST-LOVED BABY.
- YEAH.
- WE'LL BE HERE TO BACK YOU UP,
NO MATTER WHAT.
- THAT'S ALL THAT MATTERS.
- YEAH, EVERYTHING HAPPENS
FOR A REASON.
THIS IS YOUR PATH.
- CONGRATS AGAIN.
- THANK YOU.
AT THE END OF THE DAY,
WITH ALL THE BULL[bleep]
AND MAKING FUN OF ME
FOR EVERYTHING,
THEY'RE ALL ACTUALLY REALLY,
REALLY HAPPY FOR ME,
AND THEY'RE THERE FOR ME
IF I NEED ANYTHING,
SO IT FEELS REALLY GOOD
TO KNOW THAT I HAVE THEM.
- THAT WAS A LOT OF NEWS
OVER A DINNER.
- YEAH.
- THAT'S A LOT TO TAKE IN.
- THIS WAS FUN, GUYS.
- IT REALLY WAS.
IT WAS GOOD TO SEE EVERYBODY.
- HAPPY TO SEE YOU GUYS.
- I'M REALLY HAPPY
YOU GUYS CAME.
- THANK YOU GUYS, THOUGH.
APPRECIATE THIS.
- THANK YOU.
- BYE.
- LOVE YOU.
- KEEP IN TOUCH.
LET'S DO DINNER OR SOMETHING.
- LOVE YOU.
- YEAH.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- THANK YOU.
- THE HOUSE LOOKS BEAUTIFUL.
- GOOD LUCK WITH THE NEW PLACE.
- BYE, SNOOKI.
BYE, SNOOKI'S BABY.
- * I'M ALL TINGLES
AND CHILLS *
- I THOUGHT JENNI
WOULD BE THE ONE
TO ANNOUNCE AN ENGAGEMENT FIRST,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- SORRY IF I SAID
ANYTHING WEIRD.
- YOU'VE BEEN SAYING THINGS
LIKE THAT THIS WHOLE TIME.
- I GOTTA THINK
BEFORE I SAY.
I AM REALLY EXCITED
FOR YOU,
EVEN THOUGH
IT COMES OUT WEIRD.
- OH, WELL.
- * OH, OH, OH,
OH, OH, OH *
* OH, OH, OH, OH,
- CAN I SHOW YOU
A BABY COMING OUT?
- REALLY?
- YEAH.
- I DON'T KNOW IF
I'M PREPARED FOR THIS.
AM I GONNA HAVE NIGHTMARES?
- MAYBE.
SO, YOU KNOW,
I'M REALLY INTRIGUED
ABOUT BIRTH NOW,
BECAUSE OBVIOUSLY,
I'M GOING TO HAVE A BABY.
OH, HERE.
"LIVE BIRTH, NATURAL."
- WILL INSERT THE MEDICATION
INTO YOUR VAGINA
TO HELP YOUR CERVIX...
[laughter]
- [laughs]
THE WORD "VAGINA."
- LOOK, LOOK, LOOK!
JUST SEEING BABIES
POP OUT OF VAGINAS,
IT'S JUST SO CRAZY.
THAT'S A BIG VAGINA.
- DUDE, LOOK AT HER HAND.
IT, LIKE, GOT SUCKED
IN THERE.
I'M WATCHING A VAGINA,
AND I HAD NO IDEA
HOW [bleep] FAR
IT STRETCHES.
- CHERYL IS ONLY
3 CENTIMETERS DILATED.
- "ONLY."
- [laughs]
- OH, REALLY?
YOU DON'T SEE A VAGINA?
- AAH!
- LIKE, IT WENT FROM, LIKE,
OH, HERE'S THE HEAD,
HERE'S THE SHOULDERS.
YOU'VE GOT SIX MONTHS TO GET
THAT--THOSE KEGELS GOING.
- DO YOU DO YOUR KEGELS?
- YEAH.
- WHY?
- IT KEEPS IT [bleep].
[laughs]
- YOU'RE A SLUT.
- I HAVE A TINY [bleep]
AND I LOVE IT.
[laughs]
- MY DAD'S NEXT TO YOU!
- HE KNOWS I HAVE A TINY PENIS.
HE KNOWS.
I'VE HAD CHLAMYDIA FOUR TIMES,
AND I'LL TELL EVERYBODY HERE.
[upbeat music]
* *
- I'M SO OVERDOING THE COUCH.
I HAVEN'T GONE TO THE GYM.
I HAVEN'T GONE TANNING.
- I'VE GONE TO THE GYM.
- I HAVEN'T DONE MY NAILS.
I WAKE UP
THINKING ABOUT PARTIES
AND WHAT TO GET
FOR THIS STUPID HOUSE.
TODAY, WE'RE HAVING
OUR BIG HOUSEWARMING PARTY.
- SO WE'RE INVITING FRIENDS
AND FAMILY HERE
TO CELEBRATE, FINALLY,
OUR FINISHED APARTMENT.
[phone ringing]
I'M NOT HERE.
- [gasps]
ANTHONY AGAIN.
- OH, MY GOD,
JUST ANSWER IT.
- I'M NOT ANSWERING THAT.
- LEAVE A SEXY MESSAGE.
- BITCHES.
- BYE.
- HEY, LADIES.
UH, IT'S ANTHONY.
JUST TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT'S GOING ON.
YOU KNOW, I NEED TO GET MONEY,
ALL RIGHT?
UH, GIVE ME A CALL BACK
SO I CAN GET PAID, ALL RIGHT?
THANK YOU.
- I'LL CALL HIM
WHEN BRIAN'S HERE
SO WE'LL FEEL SAFE WITH
OUR NEW MAINTENANCE MAN HERE.
COOL?
- YEP.
[doorbell rings]
- COMING.
HEY.
- SO SORRY, I GOT CAUGHT UP.
SO BRIAN, OUR HANDYMAN
FROM YESTERDAY,
IS COMING BACK OVER AGAIN
TO FINISH WHAT HE STARTED.
- I LOVE BRIAN.
NOT SO MUCH ANTHONY.
OH, THAT LOOKS NICE.
- YOU LOOK LIKE
A BUNCH OF HUNTERS.
- LOOKS LIKE WE SKINNED
EVERYTHING.
- EV--EVERY ANIMAL.
- WE'RE ANIMAL LOVERS.
[doorbell rings]
[knocks on door]
- I'M NOT ANSWERING.
- ANSWER IT WITH ME.
- COME ON.
[doorbell rings]
[knocks]
- [gasps] OH, MY GOD,
IT'S ANTHONY.
- CRICKETS.
[knocks]
JENNI, ANSWER.
I'M SCARED.
I JUST THINK ANTHONY
IS REALLY CREEPY
BECAUSE HE WANTS HIS MONEY--
[belches]
OH, MY GOD.
UH.
BUT HE JUST MADE A MESS
OF EVERYTHING.
I'M SCARED.
- LOOK AT THESE THINGS.
THESE DOGS.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK IT IS?
- OH, AN INVOICE?
- YEAH, WELL, ACTUALLY,
I DIDN'T EVEN
WRITE IT DOWN YET
'CAUSE I WAS RUNNING AROUND
LIKE A MANIAC.
YOU KNOW, I GOTTA--
YOU DON'T HAVE A PEN?
- I DON'T HAVE A PEN.
- YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
WHERE IS IT? OH, HERE,
YOU WANT A LOLLIPOP?
- NO.
UGH!
HE JUST, LIKE, WENT ONE UP
ON THE FREAK SCALE.
DO YOU HAVE A PEN?
- I DO.
- LOOK AT THAT.
- THANK YOU.
- YOU'RE WELCOME.
ANTHONY, THE HANDYMAN
THAT SUCKED,
IS WATCHING THE SAVIOR
FIX HIS [bleep].
I LOVE THIS.
IT'S SO AWKWARD.
[upbeat music]
* *
[doorbell rings]
- HI, BUBBIE!
JIONNI'S HERE,
AND HE BROUGHT SOME HOT DOGS
AND HAMBURGERS
AND SHRIMP, AND HE BROUGHT US
THE BARBECUE,
AND WE'RE GONNA SET IT UP
TOGETHER.
- WHAT THE [bleep]?
- SHOULD I CALL OUR HANDYMAN?
- NO.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- WHERE'S JIONNI?
- HI.
- THAT'S IN THE THING.
- HEY, HEY.
- ROGER!
WE'RE DOING SOMETHING
RIGHT NOW.
- OH, ARE YOU? OH,
YOU'RE PUTTING THIS TOGETHER?
I'D SAY THAT TAKES YOU FOUR TO
SIX HOURS TO PUT THAT TOGETHER.
- WE'RE DONE.
- NO, WE JUST STARTED,
AND IT'S AL--ALMOST DONE.
- THIS ISN'T TIGHT.
OH, [bleep].
OH, MY GOD,
I'M [bleep] DRIPPIN'.
- IT WAS NOT GOING WELL
AT ALL,
AND IT WAS LIKE
A FIVE-YEAR-OLD KID
TRYING TO BUILD A PYRAMID.
IT WAS CRAZY.
- I JUST HAVE TO GET THIS
ON THERE.
- TAKE YOUR TIME, MAN.
- COME ON, YOU [bleep]--
- WHO, ME?
- NO.
[upbeat music]
* *
- MAYBE I DO LIKE
THIS LIPSTICK.
- I DON'T HEAR ANY CLANKING
GOING ON OUT THERE.
IS HE PUTTING IT TOGETHER?
- NO IDEA.
- ROGER?
IS ROGER HERE?
[dog barks]
- OH, GOD.
[groans]
STILL FIGURING
THIS THING OUT?
- YOU TELL ME.
- THAT'S WHY I SAID
BUY AN ASSEMBLED GRILL.
- I KNEW PUTTING THIS
GRILL TOGETHER
WAS GONNA BE A LITTLE TOUGH,
BUT NOTHING WAS FITTING RIGHT.
- THIS GOES DOWN THROUGH HERE,
NITWIT, LIKE THAT.
WHAT, DID YOU JUST THINK
IT BALANCED ON THERE?
- OH.
- LOOK OUT, YOU DUMBASS.
GOD, YOU'RE IN--
YOU'RE THE ONE IN COLLEGE.
[groans]
- UH-OH, HERE WE GO.
- BRO, DO YOU WANT
TO GET KICKED IN THE BALLSACK?
- [laughs]
- WHY IS HE GONNA KICK YOU
IN THE BALLSACK?
- I DON'T GOTTA EXPLAIN MYSELF
TO THIS KID.
- ARE YOU GUYS REALLY FIGHTING
OUT HERE OR FAKE FIGHTING?
- NO, I'M KICKING YOU
IN THE BALLS.
- GO GET HIM A STOOL, BABY,
SO HE CAN KICK ME IN THE BALLS.
[laughter]
- I COULD EASILY KICK YOU
IN THE HEAD IF I WANTED TO.
- [laughs]
OH, MY GOD.
- WITH WHAT, THOSE THINGS?
- I COULD--I COULD DEFINITELY
KICK YOU IN THE HEAD.
- SO, YOU KNOW,
JIONNI'S A WRESTLER.
HE THINKS THAT HE'S
A LITTLE BIT OF A BADASS,
BUT I'M 6'3".
YOU KNOW,
THERE'S NO WAY
THIS KID'S GONNA
KICK ME IN THE HEAD.
OKAY, THIS IS WHERE
MY HEAD WOULD BE.
KICK ME IN THE HEAD.
- I'M GONNA FALL.
- COME ON,
[bleep] CHUCK NORRIS.
- NO FIGHTING TONIGHT.
- MOVE THAT WAY MORE.
- PLEASE, IF THERE'S A GOD
UP THERE, LET HIM GET HURT.
- I HAVEN'T STRETCHED.
- LOOK-- [laughs]
- ROGER'S BUSTING MY BALLS,
AND, LIKE, YOU KNOW WHAT?
HERE'S HOW I GET ROGER BACK--
KICKING IN THE HEAD.
- YOU SAY THAT YOU CAN DO THIS.
COME ON.
OW!
- [laughs] YES!
YES! YES!
- OH!
- YOU KNOW,
NOTHING MAKES ME HAPPIER
THAN WHEN YOU GET HURT.
- SON OF A--
I JUST BOUGHT THESE SOCKS.
[hip-hop music]
**
[doorbell rings]
- OH, MAYBE THAT'S NICK.
COMING!
- WORDS I'VE NEVER HEARD
BEFORE.
- YAY!
- HOW'S IT GOIN'?
- SO EXCITED.
- WHAT'S THIS?
- IT'S OUR PAINTINGS, BOO.
- SHUT UP.
- ARE YOU EXCITED?
- SO SORRY FOR THE DELAY.
- OH, WHO CARES?
- [gasps]
- SO HERE'S THE RED ONE.
[both scream]
- COOL.
- AW!
- YOU GUYS LIKE 'EM?
- YEAH.
- LOVE YOU.
- I LOVE IT.
THESE PAINTINGS, I FEEL,
ARE GONNA JUST MAKE
THE WHOLE APARTMENT,
AND IT JUST LOOKS SO SCARFACE
AND IT'S SO DOPE.
IT'S GONNA MAKE THE PLACE
LOOK AMAZING.
- THIS WAS--THIS IS PERFECT.
- THANK YOU, NICK.
- HAVE A GREAT NIGHT.
- * I'M READY TO LOSE CONTROL
TONIGHT *
- LET'S GET THIS SHOW
ON THE ROAD.
[doorbell rings]
- I FOUND A HOBO
ON THE STREET.
- YO, DAD!
HI.
- MWAH! HOW ARE YOU?
HI, NICOLE.
- HI.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD.
- MWAH!
- MY DAD'S HERE FIRST.
I KNEW HE WOULD BE,
'CAUSE HE WOULD LEAVE
12 HOURS EARLY.
- THIS PLACE IS PRETTY AWESOME.
[doorbell rings]
- HEY, HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD.
- CAN I GET THAT?
YOU ALL RIGHT?
- HELLO.
- HI.
- THIS IS COOL.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- EH, JUST TRUCKIN' ALONG.
- JOEY, MEET JOEY.
- HI, NICE TO MEET YOU.
HOW ARE YOU?
- SO WE HAVE TWO JOEYS.
MADONNA?
- MARILYN MONROE.
- MARILYN. OH, YEAH.
- JENNI'S JOEY IS SUCH A BITCH,
AND I LOVE IT.
- NICOLE'S JOEY LOOKS LIKE
A VERY BIG, TOUGH GUY,
UNTIL HE OPENS HIS MOUTH
AND TALKS
AND RAINBOWS COME OUT.
- I HEARD YOU SAY
"CREAMY ITALIAN."
THAT WAS MY NICKNAME
IN COLLEGE.
[laughs]
- I THINK EVERY GIRL SHOULD HAVE
A GAY FRIEND NAMED JOEY,
BECAUSE EVERY GUY NAMED JOEY
WHO'S GAY IS [bleep] AMAZING.
- CHEERS.
- ALL RIGHT, CHEERS.
- OH, MY GOD.
[laughs]
- [sniffs]
- WHY ARE YOU SNIFFING ME?
- I'M SORRY.
- WHY IS THAT GUY
SNIFFING ME?
[laughter]
WHY?
- THIS SUCKS.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN, SUCKS?
WHY DOES IT SUCK?
- YOU KNOW, EVERYONE CAN,
LIKE, PARTY,
AND I'M JUST SITTING HERE.
- PATRON SHOTS, J.
- SO WHAT?
- SO I DON'T LIKE
BEING AROUND THIS,
'CAUSE I CAN'T DRINK.
- I'M NOT.
- THAT'S DIFFERENT.
YOU'RE OLD.
BEING THE ONLY SOBER ONE
HERE, YOU KNOW, IT SUCKS,
'CAUSE EVERYONE'S DRUNK,
AND THEY'RE JUST HAVING
SUCH A GREAT TIME.
LIKE, I'M BORED.
- YOU'RE DOING
THE RIGHT THING, HONEY.
YOU'RE DOING
THE RIGHT THING.
- I'M GOING TO GET
JENNI'S BRONZER
AND SPRAYING IT ON MYSELF.
- WHAT'S HE DOING?
- YO, WHY CUT YOURSELF SHORT,
BRO?
GET IN THE SPRAY TAN BOOTH.
JENNI'LL SPRAY YOU DOWN.
- JENNI, SPRAY TAN HIM!
- LET'S ASSEMBLE IT!
I WANT TO GET TAN!
- JENNI!
- DO IT!
- JOEY LOVES TO HAVE
A GOOD TIME,
AND HE ALWAYS
MAKES ME LAUGH,
AND HE'S DEFINITELY DRINKING
FOR ME RIGHT NOW,
'CAUSE HE'S SO DRUNK,
AND I KNOW HE'S GONNA REGRET IT.
BUT, YOU KNOW, YOU CAN'T STOP
JOEY FROM HAVING FUN.
- TANNING!
- WHERE IS THAT TAN LINE FROM?
[laughter]
- YES!
- HE IS GIVING HIMSELF
WEDGIES
AND PULLING
HIS UNDERWEARS UP
AND PULLING HIS SHIRT UP.
- JENNI, COME ON!
- I DID IT!
I DID IT!
IT'S IN THERE.
I FEEL LIKE I SEE A BALL POP OUT
OF THE SIDE OF HIS UNDERWEAR.
IT'S JUST--
I'M JUST TOO CLOSE.
IT'S TOO CLOSE.
- DO I LOOK LIKE
A JUICEHEAD GUIDO, NICOLE?
- YOU LOOK GORGEOUS.
OH, MY GOD, DON'T FALL.
[laughter]
- I'M NOT.
WHERE'S JIONNI?
- THIS PARTY JUST
TOOK IT UP A NOTCH, HUH?
- YEAH, I KNOW.
- DO WE LOOK THE SAME TAN?
- YOU GOT ME, BUDDY.
- I'M DARKER.
- YOU DID IT.
- WHERE'S ROGER?
- UH, LET'S SEE.
I THINK YOU'RE THERE.
- JENNI.
- THIS IS A SICK PAR--
THIS IS A SICK PARTY.
- JOEY'S BUTT CRACK
IS ACTUALLY TAN NOW.
- OH, WE DON'T HAVE TO GO
TO THE LIQUOR STORE.
- THERE IT IS.
- YOU SAVED THE DAY, BRO.
[laughter]
- HI, ROGER.
- YO, WHAT'S GOING ON,
MY MAN?
- ARE YOU THINKING ABOUT ME
MORE THAN A FRIEND?
- WHAT?
- NO? WHOOPSY.
YOU'RE SCARING ME.
SO NICOLE'S JOEY SEEMS LIKE HE'S
TAKEN A LITTLE LIKING TO ME.
- SORR--RO--
"R" TO THE O-G-E-R.
- OH!
[laughter]
- WHOA!
- ARE YOU [bleep]
KIDDING ME?
[laughter]
- * MAN DOWN *
- THERE'S MORE SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW
ON THE WAY,
AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
- YOU BOUGHT THE WRONG COUCH,
BECAUSE I'M VERY FIT.
- I KNOW YOU ARE.
- VERY, VERY FIT.
THERE'S NO REASON I SHOULD HAVE
FELL FROM THE COUCH.
THAT'S IT.
- I'VE NEVER BEEN DENIED SEX
MORE OFTEN
THAN BEING IN A RELATIONSHIP
WITH JENNI.
- I DON'T EVEN THINK ROGER
REALIZES RIGHT NOW
THE AMOUNT OF SEXUAL COMMENTS
HE'S MAKING,
'CAUSE HE'S SO DRUNK.
- I HAVE A TINY [bleep]
AND I LOVE IT.
[laughs]
- ESPECIALLY RIGHT NEXT
TO MY FATHER.
- MY DAD'S NEXT TO YOU!
- HE KNOWS I HAVE A TINY PENIS.
HE KNOWS.
- I FEEL LIKE ROGER
JUST DOESN'T KNOW
WHEN ENOUGH IS ENOUGH.
- I'M SO DEADLY HONEST,
IT'S RIDICULOUS.
I'VE HAD CHLAMYDIA FOUR TIMES,
AND I'LL TELL EVERYBODY HERE.
- HE'S RIGHT NEXT TO MY DAD!
I HAVE TO PEE.
- IT'LL PROBABLY BURN
A LITTLE BIT, BUT--
[laughter]
- I'M NOT GONNA
HAVE SEX WITH YOU
IF YOU'RE GONNA KEEP
JOKING ABOUT IT.
- WHAT'S UP?
- THIS IS MORE LIKE IT.
A LITTLE BREAK
FROM THE ACTION.
- WHAT'S YOUR TAKE
ON THE GIRLS?
- I THINK IT'S AWESOME.
- I SEE THEM, UH--
- MATURING.
- YEAH.
- OH, [bleep].
all: OH!
- THEY'VE BEEN THROUGH A LOT
IN THE PAST FEW YEARS.
- THREE YEARS, IT'S AMAZING
HOW FAR THEY'VE--THEY'VE COME.
- I'M GLAD THEY BECAME
AS CLOSE OF FRIENDS AS THEY ARE.
THEY LOOK OUT FOR EACH OTHER.
- YEP.
SO ARE YOU MORE RELIEVED NOW?
- YEAH. YEAH, I AM.
- THEY'RE GROWING UP,
IN A SENSE.
- YEP.
[hip-hop music]
- ALL RIGHT,
LET'S HIT THE ROAD.
- BYE, HANDSOME.
- I LOVE YOU, BABY.
- I LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU TOO.
- IT IS GETTING LATE,
SO RIGHT NOW,
WE'RE WRAPPING IT UP.
EVERYBODY CAN GET
THE [bleep] OUT.
I LOVE YOU.
AND NOW IT'S TIME
TO GO TO BED.
- BYE.
OH, MY GOD, IT'S TIME.
I CAN FINALLY
SMUSH JIONNI.
I'VE BEEN WAITING
ALL [bleep] NIGHT.
YOU'RE GRILLING?
- JUST TWO BURGERS.
YOU WANT ANYTHING?
- I WANT TO [bleep] CUDDLE.
- ALL RIGHT, I PROMISE,
WE'RE GONNA CUDDLE.
- USUALLY,
WHEN YOU ARE PREGNANT,
YOU JUST WANT NOTHING
TO DO WITH SEX,
BUT I'M ACTUALLY STARTING
TO GET MY SEX DRIVE BACK,
AND NOW HE WANTS
TO COOK BURGERS
AND HANG OUT WITH ROGER.
I MEAN...
WHATEVER.
DO WHAT YOU GOTTA DO.
- DO YOU KNOW WHAT I WANT
RIGHT NOW,
MORE THAN ANYTHING?
- VAGINA?
- NO, I WANT A REMATCH AT YOU
KICKING MY HAND
AT MY HEAD HEIGHT.
- I'M NOT DRUNK.
IT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
- YOU CAME UP, LIKE,
A FOOT SHORT.
- CAN YOU REACH MY HEAD?
CAN YOU REALLY REACH MY HEAD?
- SERIOUSLY, BRO.
- NO, I'M BEING SERIOUS.
A GUY YOUR SIZE,
CAN YOU REACH MY HEAD?
- ARE YOU GIVING ME PERMISSION
TO KICK YOU IN YOUR HEAD?
- YOU CAN'T KICK MY HEAD.
WHAT, ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
- ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
- GOOD. ALL RIGHT, GOOD.
YOU KICK MY HAND RIGHT NOW.
- NO, YOUR HEAD.
CAN I KICK YOU IN YOUR HEAD?
- GO AHEAD, GO AHEAD.
- CAN I KICK YOU IN YOUR HEAD?
- GO AHEAD.
OH, [bleep], IF ROGER
KICKS ME IN THE HEAD,
I MIGHT BE IN TROUBLE HERE.
- JIONNI.
- I PROMISE, GO AHEAD.
- I'M GONNA BREAK THIS KID
LIKE A TWIG,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- GO AHEAD.
THIS'LL BE GOOD.
- IN YOUR HEAD? OKAY.
[laughs]
- THAT WAS MY SHOULDER.
- ALL RIGHT,
CAN I GO AGAIN?
- NO, ARE YOU
OUT OF YOUR MIND?
THERE'S A GOOD CHANCE,
HE HIT ME IN THE HEAD,
I WASN'T GETTING UP.
HE JUST KICKED ME.
- ARE YOU HURT?
- NAH, HE HIT ME
ON A GOOD SPOT.
- [laughs]
- OH, MY GOD.
I'M SO OVER SMUSHING
WITH JIONNI.
I MEAN, I'VE BEEN WAITING
THIS WHOLE NIGHT,
AND I'M JUST LIKE,
"[bleep] IT."
LIKE, YOU KNOW,
WE WON'T EVEN CUDDLE.
OH, MY GOD.
- GOOD NIGHT, KIDS.
[sighs]
- STOP.
- STOP IT.
- I JUST WANT TO SNUGGLE.
- THEN SNUGGLE.
- OW!
- OH, SORRY.
WHEN ME AND JIONNI SMUSH,
IT'S NOT LIKE SEX.
IT'S LIKE WE'RE IN LOVE
AND IT'S VERY PASSIONATE.
IT'S NOT, LIKE,
RANDOM RABBIT SEX.
IT'S LIKE REAL SEX.
- [faint]
BABE...
BABY...
YET ANOTHER NIGHT FOR ME
OF NOT GETTING LAID.
OH, MY GOD.
- I'M VOLUNTEERING TODAY.
OH, MY GOD, THERE'S JUMPERS.
AAH!
[laughs]
HELLO.
WAAH!
- DO YOU THINK IT'S FAIR
THAT YOU JUST CONSTANTLY
BULL[bleep] ME
AND LIE TO ME?
- I DON'T BULL[bleep]
AND LIE TO YOU, ROGER.
- WOW.
JUST DON'T LIE.
IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
- WHAT'S GOING ON
RIGHT NOW?