- YOU INSULT
MY INTELLIGENCE.
- I'M NOT THOUGH!
LISTEN TO WHAT YOU'RE ACTUALLY
MAD OVER, OVER THE FACT--
- THAT I'M BEING LIED TO!
THAT I'M BEING LIED TO!
THAT'S WHAT I'M MAD OVER!
- I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
- SINCE WE'RE WITH THE BOYS
ALL THE TIME,
MAYBE IT SHOULD BE
A GIRLS' WEEKEND.
- I LIKE THAT IDEA.
- CANCUN!
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT, I LOVE IT *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
[upbeat music]
- [vocalizing]
* *
- 6:00 A.M. IS USUALLY THE TIME
THAT I GO TO BED IN SEASIDE,
SO TO BE WAKING UP RIGHT NOW,
IT FEELS WEIRD.
BUT THEN AGAIN,
WE'RE GOING TO CANCUN,
SO IT FEELS COOL.
- OH, MY GOD.
- WHAT?
I'M SPRAY TANNING THE--
OH, MY GOD,
LOOK AT MY FEET.
- EW!
YOU'RE A [bleep] WEIRDO.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
IT'S A SPRAY TAN.
- I'M NOT HANGING OUT
WITH YOU.
- DON'T LET TSA
TAKE OFF MY SOCKS.
- YOU DON'T HAVE
TO TAKE OFF YOUR SOCKS.
[doorbell rings]
- YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
- COME IN!
- MORNING!
- GOOD MORNING.
- HI!
- OH, MY GOD.
- ARE YOU EXCITED?
- YEAH. HI, SNOOKI.
[doorbell rings]
- MORNING!
- GOOD MORNING.
- EVERYTHING'S
FALLING INTO PLACE.
I WENT TANNING
AND GOT MY HAIR DONE.
- WE WENT SHOPPING.
WE PACKED.
SO WE'RE PRETTY MUCH READY
TO GO TO CANCUN.
- MM-HMM.
- CABS ARE HERE.
- YAY!
- EVERYONE CHECK FOR PASSPORTS.
- OKAY, MOM.
[Latin music]
- [singing in Spanish]
* *
- I LOVE CANCUN.
I FEEL THE WEATHER
HITTING MY SKIN,
AND THE TROPICAL
RUBBING OFF ON YOU--OH!
OH!
- AH!
- OH, SO CLASSY.
- OH, MY GOD,
THE BEDS ARE SO SOFT.
BEACH PALACE
IS SO DOPE RIGHT NOW.
THE SUITE THAT ME AND THE GIRLS
HAVE IS UNBELIEVABLE.
IT'S JUST PERFECT.
OH, MY GOD,
LOOK AT OUR VIEW.
- OH, MY GOD.
- WE'RE IN CANCUN!
- AAH!
- THE WATER IS JUST
CRYSTAL BLUE.
YOU COULD SEE
RIGHT THROUGH IT.
YOU KNOW, YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE ON A TROPICAL ISLAND.
AND WE KIND OF ARE.
- [singing in Spanish]
- READY?
- UHH!
- DO WE HAVE OUR KEYS?
- YEAH, I HAVE THE KEYS.
- THE SUN'S PERFECT
RIGHT HERE.
- THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
- RIGHT HERE.
- FOUR CHAIRS AND A MENU--
- AND A BAR RIGHT THERE.
- AND DRINKS.
- EVEN BETTER.
- I JUST WANT TO, LIKE,
MOVE TO A TROPICAL ISLAND
AND LIVE THERE.
- MOVE HERE.
- NO, I WANT TO MOVE
TO A TROPICAL ISLAND.
- THIS IS TROPICAL.
- IT'S NOT AN ISLAND.
- CANCUN'S NOT AN ISLAND?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- [belches]
[upbeat music]
* *
- RYDER, IS JENNI
IN THE SHOWER?
DO YOU KNOW?
- MM-MM.
- AAH!
- [laughs]
- WHY'D SHE JUST SCREAM?
SOMEONE WALK IN ON HER?
- OH, MY GOD.
- WHAT, MAMA?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- I'M IN THE DARK!
- [laughs]
- STOP PLAYING WITH ME
RIGHT NOW!
- GET OUT AND PUT
THE LIGHT ON.
THERE'S NO LIGHTS OUT HERE.
OH, WAIT.
DID THAT TURN ON?
- NO!
- DID THAT TURN ON?
- NO, I'M IN THE DARK!
- [laughs]
- I'M TRYING TO SHAVE
MY VAGINA, AND I CAN'T!
- [laugh] OH, MY GOD.
- BE CAREFUL WITH THAT ONE.
- THERE'S NOTHING LIKE
SHAVING YOUR CUCA
AND THE LIGHTS
[bleep] GO OUT,
AND YOU CAN'T SEE WHAT
YOUR NEXT MOVE IS GONNA BE,
AND IT COULD BE A [bleep]
DANGEROUS MOVE.
- WHAT IF YOU SHAVED
YOUR [bleep] OFF?
- HAVE YOU EVER, LIKE,
NICKED IT BEFORE?
- AAH!
THEN YOU GO PEE,
AND IT'S LIKE, EHH!
- AAH!
- JENNI,
WHERE'S YOUR FACE WASH?
- [bleep] YOU, MY FACE WASH!
OPEN THE DOOR!
- DID YOU UNLOCK IT?
I CAN'T OPEN THE DOOR.
- I CAN'T GET OUT.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE TO GO!
THE LIGHT DOESN'T WORK.
- SO WHERE'S THE FACE WASH?
- GO [bleep] YOURSELF.
- BUT I DIDN'T DO IT!
- [laughs]
- [bleep].
- OH, YOU FOUND IT!
- YES, I HAVE IT.
I COULDN'T FIND IT.
- WELL, HOW DID YOU
TURN THE LIGHT ON?
- 'CAUSE IT TURNED ON
FROM IN HERE.
I DON'T KNOW.
- [laughs]
- AAH! IT'S A MONKEY!
- WHOA!
CROCODILLY. HOLY [bleep],
IT'S, LIKE, RIGHT THERE.
- AAH!
- WHOO! WHAT WAS THAT?
- DID IT [bleep] ON ME?
- OH, MY GOD.
[upbeat music]
- SO TODAY, WE'RE GONNA HAVE
A RELAXING DAY.
HOW'S THAT, BOO?
- I WANT A FUN DAY.
- WE'RE GONNA HAVE
A YOU DAY,
SO IF YOU WANT TO RELAX
BY THE POOL,
AND THEN, IN A LITTLE BIT,
WE'RE GONNA GO TO THE ZOO.
- SO TODAY
IS MY PREGGERS DAY,
WHICH IS MY DAY,
WHERE I WANT TO GO
TO THE ZOO,
AND I WANT TO RELAX.
AND THEN TOMORROW IS JUST
A CRAZY SPRING BREAK DAY,
WHICH IS JENNI'S,
WHICH IS PROBABLY GOING
TO CONSIST OF DRINKING
AND GOING CRAZY.
- GOD, IT'S SO PRETTY.
- IS IT NICE?
- GET YOUR FEET WET.
- I DON'T WANT TO.
- DO YOU WANT TO GO
IN THE POOL?
- NO.
- NICOLE, AT THIS POINT,
IS GETTING A LITTLE REPETITIVE
WITH SAYING THAT SHE CAN'T DO
THAT, SHE CAN'T DO THIS,
AND I'M NOT SURE THAT PREGNANCY
IS SUPPOSED TO BE A HANDICAP.
I GOT SAND
IN MY VAGINA.
OH, MY GOD.
RIGHT INTO IT.
- I WANT TO EAT.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA WAIT FOR THEM?
- THEY'RE HAVING FUN.
I'M GONNA JUST JUMP
IN THE CLEAN WATER.
- I WISH WE CAME HERE
BEFORE I GOT PREGNANT.
- THAT'S TRUE.
- I HAD [bleep] ABS.
I WAS RIPPED.
- WHO CARES?
BUT YOU ARE PREGNANT.
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU'RE FAT.
- YEAH, BUT IT LOOKS FAT.
- BUT EVERYONE KNOWS
YOU'RE PREGNANT.
- I DON'T CARE.
WELL, IT'S DEFINITELY
EASY FOR JENNI
TO JUST, YOU KNOW,
SAY ALL THESE THINGS,
LIKE, "YOU SHOULD SHOW OFF
YOUR STOMACH,"
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH,
BUT, BITCH, LET'S GET REAL.
IF YOU WERE PREGNANT
AND YOUR BODY WAS CHANGING,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA
SHOW THAT [bleep] OFF.
[upbeat music]
I WANT TO GO TO THE ZOO.
I'M SO BORED.
- WELL, WHAT ELSE
DO YOU WANT TO DO?
- I WANT TO GO TO THE ZOO!
- TEQUILA?
- SHOT?
- THIS IS SO AWESOME.
[all speaking Spanish]
- THIS IS SUPPOSED TO BE MY DAY,
PREGGERS DAY,
AND THE GIRLS ARE DRINKING.
THEY'RE DOING SHOTS.
AND I'M LIKE,
"COOL [bleep] PREGGERS DAY."
I DON'T WANT
ANY MORE SUN.
[laughter]
- NOW IT'S SPRING BREAK.
- JENNI?
- HUH?
- CAN WE GO SOON?
I WANT TO GO TO THE ZOO.
- I JUST WANT TO DO MY BACK
FOR, LIKE, 20.
- [sighs]
- BOO, I'M GOING TO STEP IN,
LIKE, A STORE INSIDE OUR HOTEL.
- SO WE'RE GOING?
- YEAH.
- MM, THANK GOD.
[Latin music]
* *
- I LIKE YOUR STUFF.
DO YOU HAVE
THREE MORE OF THESE?
I FIND THESE CROCODILE HATS
AT OUR SOUVENIR SHOP,
AND I'M LIKE, "DUDE,
WE HAVE TO WEAR THESE
TO THE CROCODILE ZOO."
LIKE, LET'S PLAY IT UP
A LITTLE BIT.
[beep]
- IT'S CROC DAY. YAY.
I'M HAPPY NOW.
HE LOOKS LIKE A BOY,
DOESN'T HE?
READY FOR THE ZOO?
GONNA MEET YOUR PARENTS.
- NICOLE'S BRINGING CROCODILLY
TO THE CROCODILE ZOO,
SO HE CAN MEET HIS FAMILY...
'CAUSE THAT'S WHAT
TEN-YEAR-OLDS DO.
WEAR A HAT.
- WHOO-HOO.
- [laughs]
- GOT EVERYTHING?
- MY EXPECTATIONS
AT THE ZOO--
I MEAN,
THEY'RE SO [bleep] HIGH
BECAUSE I'M SO EXCITED
JUST TO SEE THE ALLIGATORS
AND THE CROCODILLIES
AND MONKEYS, AND, YOU KNOW,
I [bleep] LOVE ZOOS.
- OKAY, READY?
MY NAME IS JONATHAN.
I'M GONNA BE
YOUR TOUR GUIDE.
WE'RE GONNA SEE WILD MONKEYS,
RIGHT?
SO MONKEYS, UH, JUST FEEDING,
NO TOUCHING,
BECAUSE THEY CAN REACT
AGGRESSIVE.
- OH, [bleep].
AAH, IT'S A MONKEY!
- WHOA!
I HAD NO IDEA THAT
THIS PLACE HAD MONKEYS FREE,
LIKE, JUST ROAMING AROUND,
GOING CRAZY.
THEY COULD PULL YOUR HAIR,
TOUCH YOUR HAIR.
I GOT SCARED.
- AAH!
- RECOMMENDATION--
- [screaming]
- WHOA!
LOOKS LIKE
A [bleep] ALIEN!
- IF YOU GET TOO CLOSE,
HE WILL JUMP OVER YOU,
PULL YOUR HAIR.
- OH, NO, BITCH.
YOU DON'T PULL MY EXTENSIONS.
- [laughs]
- OH, MY GOD.
- ALL RIGHT.
- THEY'RE WRESTLING.
OR ARE THEY HAVING SEX?
- NO, TOO YOUNG TO HAVE SEX.
- NEVER TOO YOUNG
TO HAVE SEX.
- ROLE MODEL.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S MOVE
A LITTLE BIT OVER THERE.
WE HAVE THREE GIRLS RIGHT HERE
AND ONE BOY.
THE BOY IS VERY CAMOUFLAGED
RIGHT NOW.
- DOES THE BOY BANG
ALL TWO GIRLS OR THREE GIRLS?
- YEAH, RIGHT NOW,
THEY'RE PREGNANT. [laughs]
- ALL OF THEM?
- THE GIRLS ARE?
- THERE'S ONLY TWO.
- WHAT? OH.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE BANGS
ALL THREE LIZARDS.
- OH, IT'S GOT A FAUXHAWK.
- UHH!
- OH, MY GOD, IT DOES. HI!
- LITTLE BABY FAUXHAWK.
- AW, IT LOOKS
LIKE A GUIDO.
- LET'S GO OVER HERE
TO A TREE.
WE HAVE SOME PARROTS
FROM MEXICO RIGHT HERE.
- WHERE'S
THE NORMAL PAVEMENT?
IT FEELS LIKE
[bleep] ITALY.
THIS ZOO IS LIKE
A SAFARI,
AND I LOVE, LIKE,
THE REAL [bleep],
AND THIS IS DEFINITELY REAL.
- [gasps]
- UHH!
EW, IT LOOKS LIKE
A VAGINA.
- I WAS JUST ABOUT
TO SAY THAT.
- NOW LOOK INSIDE.
- I CANNOT EXPLAIN TO YOU
THE FEAR I HAVE WITH CROCODILES,
AND I'M ACTUALLY TRYING TO
CONQUER MY FEAR RIGHT NOW,
BUT I THINK I'M ACTUALLY
[bleep] MYSELF AT THE SAME TIME.
- WAIT FOR ME
JUST A SECOND HERE.
I'M GOING TO CLOSE THE DOOR.
- HOLY [bleep],
IT'S, LIKE, RIGHT THERE.
- OH, MY GOD, I DIDN'T EVEN
REALIZE THAT ONE.
- CROCODILLY.
- THERE'S ONE WALKING THIS WAY.
- THERE'S ONE WALKING TO US.
THEY'RE SCARING US.
- HERE HE COMES,
HERE HE COMES.
- I FEEL LIKE JURASSIC PARK
RIGHT NOW.
I FEEL LIKE THIS ZOO
IS JUST A LITTLE BIT DIFFERENT
THAN AN AMERICAN ZOO.
I MEAN, THERE'S A BARRIER WHEN
IT COMES TO AN AMERICAN ZOO,
AND IT'S JUST
A FREE-FOR-ALL HERE.
- ARE THESE REINDEER?
WHOA! WHY ARE THEY OVER HERE?
- [laughs] OKAY.
- THE GATE'S OPEN.
- I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU THIS.
DID YOU WANT TO FEED THEM?
- OH, I'M--OH.
OH, HELL NO!
HELL NO!
- AAH!
- HELL NO!
- OH, MY GOD.
- GUYS, STAY QUIET,
STAY QUIET.
- OH, MY GOD.
[animal screeching]
- WHAT THE [bleep]
IS GOING ON?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- WE'RE [bleep].
- WHOO!
[animal screeches]
GOD.
[hisses]
- LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
- THERE WAS A STAMPEDE.
[laughs]
- THE FACT THAT
THE GIRLS CAME
AND THEY HAD AN AMAZING TIME
AT THE ZOO, JUST LIKE I DID,
AND THERE WASN'T
ANY DRINKING INVOLVED,
AND IT'S MORE OF EXPLORING
AND ENJOYING CANCUN,
YOU KNOW,
IT MEANT A LOT TO ME.
WHOA!
DID IT [bleep] ON ME?
- [laughs]
[hip-hop music]
- * WHOO, WHOO, YOU LIKE IT
LIKE THAT, MAMI? *
* WHOO, WHOO *
- WHAT TABLE?
- OVER THERE.
SO TONIGHT WE'RE GONNA DO
ITALIAN IN MEXICO, OBVIOUSLY.
I MEAN, JUST BECAUSE
WE'RE IN MEXICO
DOESN'T MEAN I HAVE
TO EAT MEXICAN.
I AIN'T TRYING TO GET BLOATED
BEFORE I GO TO THE CLUB.
[upbeat music]
- COOL!
- HE PROBABLY IMAGINES HE'S,
LIKE, IN A VIDEO GAME
AND LOVES LIFE.
- OH, MY GOD.
- WOW.
- THE FIRE SHOW IS DOPE.
IT STARTED OUT A LITTLE BORING,
BUT THAT [bleep]
GETTING GOOD.
DO YOU GET TAN LIKE THAT?
- NO.
I DON'T THINK YOU COULD
GET A TAN FROM TWIRLING FIRE
BECAUSE I THINK YOU NEED THE SUN
AND UV LIGHTS TO GET TAN.
[cheers and applause]
COOL, IT'S OVER.
[applause]
AW.
I HAVEN'T SEEN
A MOON HERE YET.
IS THERE A MOON
IN THIS COUNTRY?
- GOOD POINT.
- I HAVEN'T SEEN ONE YET.
- IT COULD BE ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE BUILDING.
- HELLO, MOON.
- I'LL GIVE IT TO YOU
STRAIGHT.
THERE'S A MOON IN EVERY COUNTRY,
SINCE THERE'S ONLY ONE MOON.
- I KNOW.
- BUT WHERE IT IS,
I HAVE NO IDEA.
- [imitates Jenni]
"DO YOU GET TAN FROM FIRE?"
- BURNT, I MEANT TO SAY.
- NO, YOU SAID "TAN."
[dance music]
- OH, THIS PLACE LOOKS SICK.
* *
- HOPE WE DON'T STAY OUT
TOO LATE TONIGHT.
[club music]
* *
- WE'RE GOING TO THIS CLUB,
MADALA,
AND IT'S JUST
AN OCEAN OF PEOPLE.
LIKE, IT'S, LIKE,
JUST LIKE A POD.
* *
- I MEAN, YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT
IT WAS PREGGERS DAY,
AND I NEVER SAID I WANTED
TO GO TO A CLUB,
SO I KIND OF, LIKE,
DIDN'T EVEN PLAN THE NIGHT.
THE ONLY THING I PLANNED
IN MY DAY WAS THE ZOO.
- WE'RE ONLY TAKING SHOTS,
NO DRINKS!
- SHOT?
- SHOT!
* *
- I'M BORED.
- WHAT?
- WANT ME TO GIVE YOU
A LAP DANCE?
- NO.
* *
I'M TIRED.
I DON'T KNOW
HOW TO TAKE THIS TRIP
BECAUSE OBVIOUSLY,
IF I WASN'T PREGNANT,
I'D BE STOKED
TO GO TO CANCUN,
AND I'D BE LIKE, "I'M DRINKING
THE WHOLE [bleep] TIME."
BUT NOW I'M PREGNANT,
SO, YOU KNOW,
THIS IS KIND OF LIKE
A LEARNING EXPERIENCE FOR ME,
AND I REALLY DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO EXPECT.
* *
- COME ON, YOU KNOW
YOU WANT TO DANCE.
* *
- WHERE'S THE BATHROOM?
- YOU GOTTA GO THIS WAY.
* *
- I'LL GO WITH YOU.
I GOTTA PEE.
- YOU NEED TO GO
TO THE BATHROOM?
- YEAH, BUT I'LL HOLD IT.
- BATHROOM BREAK!
* *
- I FEEL TERRIBLE
FOR LEAVING NICOLE.
I FEEL [bleep] TERRIBLE.
* *
- I DEFINITELY FEEL LIKE
THIS PLACE IS GETTING CROWDED.
* *
EVERYONE IS PSYCHOTIC,
CRAZY DRUNK.
* *
[overlapping shouting,
rock music]
ALL OF A SUDDEN,
IT'S MADNESS.
GUYS THAT DON'T EVEN
KNOW EACH OTHER ARE FIGHTING,
AND THEN, LIKE,
I SWEAR TO GOD,
AN ELBOW CRACKS ME
IN MY EYE.
MY EYE!
GET ME OUT OF HERE!
- I'M LIKE, ABOUT TO CRY
IN TEARS,
BECAUSE I'M, LIKE,
SERIOUSLY,
"I SHOULDN'T BE HERE."
THERE'S A FIGHT BREAKING OUT.
YOU KNOW, GOD FORBID SOMEONE
BUMPED INTO ME,
AND, YOU KNOW, I GOT HURT
AND LOST THE BABY.
LIKE, I DON'T NEED TO BE
IN DANGER LIKE THAT.
- THERE'S MORE SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW
ON THE WAY,
AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
[club music]
- I'M JUST MAD TIRED,
AND THEN THE FIGHT
JUST HAPPENED.
I'M IN A DIFFERENT MINDSET
THAN ALL OF YOU.
LIKE, GOD FORBID SOMETHING
HIT ME IN THE STOMACH,
AND I HAD A MISCARRIAGE.
LIKE, THIS ISN'T
MY SCENE RIGHT NOW.
I'M [bleep] ENGAGED,
AND I'M FOUR MONTHS PREGNANT.
LET'S BE SERIOUS.
I HONESTLY THINK I'M JUST
NOT THINKING STRAIGHT,
AND I'M NOT BEING RESPONSIBLE
ABOUT BEING PREGNANT,
AND I--I'M KIND OF PISSED OFF
AT MYSELF FOR IT.
IT'S [bleep] 2:00
IN THE MORNING.
I SHOULDN'T BE HERE!
- COME ON!
TODAY WAS YOUR DAY!
YOU COULD HAVE SAID NO!
- LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
- SO NICOLE WANTS TO GO,
AND I REALLY WANTED TO STAY,
BUT IT IS HER NIGHT,
SO I'LL JUST MAKE SURE
I GO HARDER TOMORROW.
- LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
- YOU KNOW BEACH PALACE?
* *
- DOLPHIN DAY! DOLPHIN DAY!
DOLPHIN DAY! DOLPHIN DAY!
- STOP. I HAVE TO PEE.
- LET'S GO.
- I'M ACTUALLY VERY EXCITED
TO SEE THE DOLPHINS
BECAUSE I SWAM
WITH DOLPHINS BEFORE,
AND IT'S [bleep] AMAZING,
AND, YOU KNOW,
IT PUTS EVERYONE
IN A GOOD MOOD
AND ALSO BECAUSE
WE'RE NOT DRINKING
SO THAT I CAN,
YOU KNOW,
BE A PART OF SOMETHING
WITH THE GIRLS.
- WELCOME TO
DOLPHIN DISCOVERY!
ARE YOU READY?
- YEAH!
[laughs] OOH!
- [speaking Spanish]
[applause]
- WHOO!
- OH!
- EXCELLENT!
- AAH!
- [laughs]
[cheering]
- EXCELLENT.
VERY NICE.
- I LOVE THAT.
I'LL NEVER GET HOW THESE
DOLPHINS ARE THIS TRAINABLE.
LIKE, MY DOGS CAN'T EVEN [bleep]
PISS ON A WEE-WEE,
AND YET DOLPHINS
CAN DANCE IN THE WATER.
- WHOO!
- AAH! HIGHER!
- AAH!
- HIGHER. THAT'S RIGHT.
- I GOT BITCH-SMACKED
BY A DOLPHIN!
- I MEAN,
I'M NOT EVEN THINKING
ABOUT LAST NIGHT
BEING A BUZZKILL
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
I'M HAVING SUCH A GREAT TIME
WITH THE ANIMALS,
AND THAT'S, YOU KNOW,
REALLY THE ONLY THING
THAT I WANT TO DO ON THIS TRIP.
[upbeat music]
BYE.
OH, IT WAVED!
BYE!
[whimsical music]
- HI, CAN YOU SEND UP
A BOTTLE OF ABSOLUT?
THANK YOU.
[hangs up phone receiver]
- SINCE WHEN DID YOU
BECOME FUN?
- [laughs]
- 'CAUSE I'M PRETTY SURE YOU
NEVER DRANK WITH ME LIKE THIS.
WHO THE [bleep]
IS THIS GIRL?
BECAUSE BEFORE I WAS PREGNANT,
SHE NEVER WANTED TO GO OUT,
SHE NEVER WANTED TO DRINK,
AND NOW THAT I'M PREGNANT,
ALL OF A SUDDEN, SHE'S FUN.
I'M LIKE, COOL, LIKE,
WHERE WERE YOU
THE PAST THREE YEARS
THAT I KNEW YOU?
- LET ME JUST TRY
THE OTHER SHIRT ON REAL QUICK.
- BUT OF COURSE,
WHEN I'M PREGNANT,
THAT'S WHEN YOU'RE FUN.
- OH, MY GOD!
- YEAH, COOL.
- I KIND OF DO TAKE
OFFENSE TO THE FACT
THAT NICOLE THINKS
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
I'VE EVER PARTIED AND HAD FUN.
TECHNICALLY, THIS JENNI
HAS ALWAYS BEEN HERE,
BUT NICOLE WAS TOO BLACKOUT
TO NOTICE.
WE'RE LEAVING!
WE'RE IN THE ELEVATOR!
- WHATEVER.
- NICOLE!
YOU GO.
- I FEEL LIKE IF
SHE DOESN'T WANT TO GO,
SHE DOESN'T GIVE A [bleep].
- YEAH, BUT SHE DOESN'T
HAVE ANY CONSIDERATION
FOR ANYBODY ELSE
WHO WANTS TO GO.
LIKE, WHY MAKE OUR LIVES
MISERABLE
JUST BECAUSE YOU DON'T
WANT TO BE HERE?
- STOP SCREAMING AT ME.
- WELL, YOU'RE LATE.
- THEN GO WITHOUT ME.
I REALLY DON'T CARE.
- WE'RE NOT GONNA GO
WITHOUT YOU.
BE CONSIDERATE.
- I AM.
YOU BE CONSIDERATE.
I'M PREGNANT, AND WE'RE ALL,
"WHOO!"
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO GO.
- THEN DON'T.
- NO, 'CAUSE I'M NOT
GONNA SIT IN THE ROOM BY MYSELF.
SOMETIMES WHEN YOU'RE PREGNANT,
YOU GET IN THESE MOODS
WHERE YOU DON'T [bleep]
LIKE ANYONE,
AND, YOU KNOW, I'M KIND OF
TAKING IT OUT ON JENNI.
- I JUST WANT TO DANCE
TONIGHT.
I WANNA HEAR
GOOD MUSIC.
- DURING THE WHOLE DINNER,
I'M CONTEMPLATING WHETHER
I SHOULD GET UP OR STAY.
I MEAN, AT THIS POINT,
I JUST WANT NOTHING TO DO
WITH THE GIRLS,
AND I JUST DEFINITELY
WANT TO LEAVE CANCUN NOW.
- CHEERS.
- OH, GOD.
[bleep].
- DON'T MAKE THAT--YEAH,
DON'T GIVE ME THAT FACE.
- SORRY THAT SHE'S PREGNANT
BECAUSE I'M TRYING TO GO
HARD AS I CAN.
I MEAN, IT'S CANCUN.
ARE YOU ANNOYED?
- NO.
- TIRED?
- I'M NOT GOING OUT, SO...
- DEALING WITH NICOLE
IN CANCUN SUCKS.
LIKE, I WISH
SHE DIDN'T COME.
IT WASN'T MEANT TO BE
FOR HER.
- THANK YOU.
- NIGHT.
- UM, GO, GO, GO, GO.
HOLA.
- YEAH!
[laughs]
- YOU'RE STILL COLD?
- JUST FOR A COUPLE MINUTES.
ARE YOU STAYING?
- YEAH.
- NICOLE IS NOT
GOING OUT TONIGHT,
AND I AM NOT
ASKING HER WHY
BECAUSE IT IS MY NIGHT,
AND I REFUSE TO MAKE NICOLE
STAY WITH ME OUT THE WHOLE TIME.
[line ringing]
- I FEEL BAD.
SHE INVITED ME HERE.
[line ringing]
- THIS TRIP WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
AMAZINGLY FUN WITH MY FRIENDS,
BUT I JUST FEEL ALONE
AND PREGNANT
AND NO ONE THERE
TO SUPPORT ME.
I'M REALLY SAD.
[dramatic music]
I DON'T THINK I WANT TO LIVE
WITH JENNI ANYMORE.
- I DON'T KNOW
IF WE'RE COMING, BABE.
- SO YOU'RE NOT COMING?
ROGER FINALLY HAS GONE
WAY TOO FAR.
TO BE HONEST, I DON'T EVEN KNOW
IF WE'RE TOGETHER AT THIS POINT.
- THEY'RE ALL OVER HIM.
I'M, LIKE, QUESTIONING
OUR ENGAGEMENT.
LIKE, ARE YOU READY?
- I THOUGHT MAYBE
YOU WERE READY
TO BE A MOTHER
AND A--AND A--AND A WIFE.
MAYBE YOU'RE NOT.
- THAT WAS MEAN.
[hangs up phone receiver]