- I'M SORRY.
- WHY'RE YOU ALL DRESSED UP?
- 'CAUSE IT'S YOUR BIRTHDAY.
SORRY.
- WHAT THE--
IT'S NOT FUNNY.
I'M TRYING TO BE MAD AT YOU.
ROGER MAKES ME LAUGH,
AND THAT'S WHY I LOVE HIM.
BUT HE DRIVES ME
[bleep] NUTS.
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT
I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
[mellow guitar music]
* *
- * WHEN WILL THE SPRING
COME AGAIN *
* WHEN WILL FLOWERS PUSH UP
AND BLOW IN THE WIND *
* WHEN WILL THE SPRING
COME AGAIN *
- NOTHING WAS REALLY
SOLVED LAST NIGHT,
BUT ME AND ROGER
WOKE UP AMICABLY.
WE WOKE UP COOL IN A SENSE
THAT WE WEREN'T ARGUING.
WANNA GO OUT?
- WHAT DO YOU WANNA DO?
YOU WANNA GO TO BREAKFAST?
- BROWNSTONE?
I AM TELLING ROGER
WE SHOULD GO OUT TO BREAKFAST
BECAUSE I WOULD LIKE TO TALK
TO HIM ABOUT LAST NIGHT.
- NICOLE, THEY WANNA
GO OUT FOR BREAKFAST.
- I CAN'T, I HAVE TO GO
TO FRIGGIN' KINDERGARTEN.
- * WHEN WILL THE SPRING
COME AGAIN *
[kiss]
- I GOTTA LEAVE.
- BREAKFAST,
THE HAMILTON INN?
- KINDA HARD TO TALK IN THERE,
BUT, YEAH, THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
IF YOU COULDN'T TALK,
IT WOULD BE A BETTER BREAKFAST.
- I'LL KILL YOU.
- THE FOOD WOULD TASTE BETTER.
I'M JUST SAYING.
- YOU LEAVING?
- NO, I'M JUST PACKING.
NICOLE'S GOTTA GO
DO HER THING.
- YOU CAN COME OUT
TO LUNCH WITH US.
- WITH YOU AND ROGER?
- BREAKFAST. WHATEVER.
- I'D BE
YOUR [bleep] THERAPIST.
- BYE.
- HEY.
- WE'RE DYEING THE GIRLS TODAY.
SO I WANNA TEST THIS ORGANIC,
HEALTHY DYE
THAT I'M REALLY EXCITED
TO PUT ON MY DOGS,
SO THAT'S WHAT NICOLE'S
GONNA DO TODAY
WHILE SHE'S VOLUNTEERING.
SAY HI! ARE YOU EXCITED?
- COME HERE.
- ALL PINK. I THINK
WE SHOULD DO IT ALL PINK.
LIKE A PINK FLUFF BALL.
- NOT REALLY.
WE GOTTA TEST IT OUT.
I'M THINKING LIKE NOELLE'S
TAIL AND CLAWS.
- THAT'S NOT FUN.
- I LOVE YOU.
I'LL BE BACK.
- SO YOU WANNA START
WITH THE FUN STUFF?
YOU WANNA START DYEING?
- YEAH.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S DO IT.
- I DEFINITELY WANNA DYE
BELLA PINK.
AND THEN NOELLE
COULD BE LIKE A PURPLE,
BECAUSE NOELLE IS KIND OF LIKE
A TOMBOY/LESBIAN.
- AH--
- OOH--
- WHAT DID YOU DO, NICOLE?
- I DIDN'T DO IT.
CAN YOU GET IT OFF?
- [laughing]
- YOU WANNA JUST DYE HER
ALL PURPLE?
- SHOULD WE?
- YEAH.
- WILL JENNI BE MAD?
- NO.
SO I DECIDED,
SINCE I'M THE AUNT,
THAT WE SHOULD JUST DYE NOELLE
ALL PURPLE
BECAUSE...YOU KNOW,
I THINK IT WOULD BE CUTE.
YOU'RE GONNA BE PURPLE!
- I HAD A [bleep] WEEKEND.
- BY [bleep] DO YOU MEAN
OVERDRAMATIC AND SELFISH?
- I'VE BEEN OVERDRAMATIC
SINCE I WAS A KID.
- I KNOW YOU HATE
THE WORD "INSECURE,"
SO I WON'T USE IT 'CAUSE
I DON'T WANT TO BE INSULTING,
BUT YOU ARE VERY,
VERY SUSPICIOUS OF ME.
I'M JUST SAYING TRUST ME.
I DESERVE IT.
I'VE EARNED IT.
IT PISSES ME OFF WHEN YOU DON'T.
- YEAH.
WE DO HAVE A LOT
TO WORK ON.
- WITHOUT A DOUBT.
THAT'S WHY I DON'T THINK
WE'RE READY TO GET MARRIED
OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
I DO WANT TO MARRY YOU ONE DAY,
BUT WE'RE NOT READY.
- I AGREE.
- I REMEMBER THE FIRST DAY
YOU WALKED THROUGH THE DOOR.
I SAID TO MY BUDDY,
"OH, MY GOD,
THAT IS MY TYPE OF GIRL."
- SO IF YOU WOULD HAVE KNOWN
EVERYTHING ABOUT ME THEN...
- OH, I WOULD HAVE NEVER
[bleep] DATED YOU.
YOU'RE A MESS.
IT'S TOO LATE NOW.
- "I WOULD'VE NEVER DATED YOU."
- IT'S TOO LATE, I FELL IN LOVE.
I GOTTA STICK IT OUT NOW.
THESE WARS, THESE BATTLES,
IF YOU WILL, THAT WE HAVE--
THEY KIND OF HELP US OUT,
AND IT'S UNFORTUNATE
THAT YOU HAVE TO SCREAM
AND YELL TO DO IT, BUT...
YOU KNOW,
IT'S OUR WAY, I GUESS.
- I THINK LATER TONIGHT
I'M GONNA LOOK ONLINE
FOR A FAKE BABY.
- A FAKE BABY?
OH, ONE OF THOSE
LIKE ONES THAT ACTUALLY
USES THE BATHROOM--
- OH, NOT LIKE A TOYS "R" US
ONE, LIKE A LEGIT...
- AS A GAG GIFT OR AS--
- NO, I'M GONNA LEGIT SAY,
LIKE, "THIS IS WHAT YOU'RE
GONNA BE DEALING WITH
IN ABOUT 5 1/2 MONTHS."
- NEED A CRIB.
A BABY DOESN'T ACTUALLY SLEEP--
AN INFANT DOESN'T SLEEP
IN THE BED WITH YOU.
- PUT LIKE A LITTLE BASSINET
NEXT TO THE BED.
- OKAY. NICOLE'S
GONNA HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT THE WORD "BASSINET" MEANS.
- GOD.
- GONNA HAVE TO EXPLAIN
THAT ONE TO HER.
- IT LEGIT IS 16 AND PREGNANT.
I SWEAR TO GOD.
THANK YOU FOR COMING
AND TEMPORARILY FIXING US.
- [chuckles] LOVE YOU,
HATE YOU AT THE SAME TIME.
- I DON'T LIKE YOU,
BUT I LOVE YOU.
- MOSTLY HATE.
A LITTLE BIT OF LOVE IN THERE.
BYE, PSYCHO.
- BYE, [bleep].
FAKE BABY TIME.
SO I WAS THINKING ABOUT
GETTING NICOLE A FAKE BABY,
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE SHE SHOULD
PREP FOR MOTHERHOOD.
BUT LET'S GET REAL.
IT'S A FAKE BABY.
EEW!
THAT'S A LITTLE
TOO LIFELIKE!
"REALCARE BABY
MAKES IT POSSIBLE
"FOR PEOPLE TO PRACTICE
CARING FOR AN INFANT
"24 HOURS A DAY,
7 DAYS A WEEK.
WEARS UNIQUE WIRELESS I.D.
TO ENSURE ACCOUNTABILITY."
OH, YEAH.
"REALCARE ETHNICITY CHOICES."
I'D LIKE A TAN ONE.
I'D HEARD THESE ARE LIKE
THE BEST THINGS
FOR PRACTICING PARENTHOOD
OR ABSTINENCE.
IT'S A LITTLE TOO LATE
FOR THAT.
- HELLO?
- HI. MY NAME IS JENNI,
AND I HAVE A FEW QUESTIONS
THAT I SAW OFF YOUR WEBSITE
ABOUT GETTING A FAKE BABY.
- OH, YEAH, OF COURSE.
GO AHEAD.
- ARE THEY PRETTY ACCURATE
TO THE REAL THING?
- HELLO?
- [mouthing word]
- UM, THEY ARE...
- CAN I CALL YOU BACK
IN TEN MINUTES?
HI, BOO.
- HELLO.
- CAN YOU GO TO THE BATHROOM
FOR A SECOND?
- WHY?
- HELLO, ARE YOU STILL THERE?
- JUST DO IT.
IT'S A SURPRISE.
YEAH, CAN YOU HOLD ON
ONE SECOND?
- YOU'RE SURPRISING ME?
- OKAY.
- YEAH. JUST GO OUTSIDE
FOR FIVE MINUTES.
- YOU NEVER KNOW WITH JENNI.
WHEN SHE SAYS
SHE HAS A SURPRISE,
IT'S EITHER REALLY GOOD
OR IT'S A [bleep] JOKE.
- WHAT COLORS DO YOU HAVE?
- COLORS?
- YEAH.
I NEED TAN.
- TAN?
UM...WE DON'T HAVE TAN.
- SOME SORT OF OFF-WHITE?
- UM...
- SOME SORT OF SPANISH?
- LIKE BEIGE...IT'S KIND OF--
IT'S KIND OF AN OFF--
IT'S--IT'S JUST SO VEINY.
I--WELL--
- A CAUCASIAN, YOU MEAN?
- YOU COULD PROBABLY PAINT
YOUR BABY IF YOU WANTED.
- CAN I COME OUT?
- NO.
- SO TODAY IS MY APPOINTMENT,
AND I'M GONNA ASK THE DOCTOR
IF HE CAN TELL THE SEX.
- THAT'S THE BABY'S HEAD
RIGHT THERE.
- CAN WE SEE
IF IT HAS A WEINER?
- THIS IS LIKE
THE REAL DEAL.
LIKE, I AM HAVING
A BABY [bleep].
- NOW I KNOW WHAT COLOR
TO PAINT THE SPARE ROOM.
- CAN I COME OUT?
- NO!
- [grunts] UGH!
[bleep]
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
I MIGHT AS WELL JUST TAKE TWO.
- TWO COME IN THE DELUXE
PACKAGE.
- OH, THEY DO? OKAY.
I'LL TAKE THE DELUXE PACKAGE.
I'M SAYING IT
RIGHT OFF THE BAT.
I WILL PLAY ALONG
UNTIL THESE [bleep] THINGS
GET IN THE WAY
OF MY REAL LIFE.
- GOOD LUCK.
- THANK YOU.
IT AIN'T FOR ME, SO...
BYE.
- WHY ARE YOU BEING
A SHADESTER?
I HOPE IT'S NOT
A MEAN THING.
- WOULD I EVER DO
MEAN TO YOU?
- YEAH.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
WE MIGHT AS WELL
GRAB THE DOGS.
- CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
WHAT BELLA LOOKS LIKE.
HOW'S THE BITCHES LOOK?
SO THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
THAT JENNI'S GONNA SEE
NOELLE AND BELLA DYED.
I'M KINDA LIKE DYING INSIDE,
'CAUSE I REALLY WANNA LAUGH.
BUT I'M KINDA SCARED, YOU KNOW,
JENNI MIGHT PUNCH ME IN THE FACE
IF SHE SEES
WHAT I DID TO NOELLE.
- STOP WITH THE ANTICIPATION.
AAH!
[Nicole laughs]
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT DID YOU DO TO HER?
[Nicole laughing]
- SHE HAD A LOT OF FUN.
- SHE LOVED IT!
- IT'S ALL HEALTHY.
COMES OUT
IN FOUR TO SIX WASHES.
- YOU'RE [bleep] BARNEY!
- THEY LOOK LIKE SKITTLES.
- MY POOR [bleep] CHILD.
- THEY'RE LIKE--NOELLE'S
AN ACCESSORY RIGHT NOW.
- THANKS.
OH, MY GOD.
- HA HA HA!
- I DO NOT CALL MY DOGS
ACCESSORIES.
- SORRY.
- THEY'RE MY CHILDREN.
- OH. WHOOPS.
EVEN IF YOU'RE MAD AT ME,
I SAID, WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THIS IS GETTING BACK AT HER
FOR SLAPPING ME IN THE FACE
WITH PIZZA DOUGH.
- YOU GOT ME BACK.
YOU DYED MY [bleep] DOG.
[Nicole chuckles]
[doorbell rings]
- WHO IS THAT?
- NO IDEA.
- WHO IS IT?
- I HAVE A DELIVERY
FOR JENNI.
- JENNI, YOU GOT A PACKAGE.
WHAT IS THAT?
- HI.
- HI, HOW ARE YA?
- WHAT'S THAT?
- I HAVE NO IDEA.
- OH...
- HAVE A NICE DAY.
- BYE.
- NOW YOU HAVE A PACKAGE.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
- A PRESENT?
- MM-HMM.
- FROM YOU?
- IT'S LIKE, OH, COOL,
SHE GOT ME SOMETHING
FOR THE BABY!
WHAT A SWEET FRIEND.
IS THIS A [bleep] BABY?
- GOOD LUCK.
[laughs]
- WHY'D YOU GET TWO BABIES?
I'M NOT HAVING TWINS.
- I SAID [bleep] IT.
I MIGHT AS WELL GET MYSELF ONE.
- EEW! IT HAS A WEINER!
- THAT'S WHAT MALE BABIES HAVE.
- DOESN'T EVEN LOOK LIKE
A GUIDO.
- I ASKED FOR TAN.
THEY DIDN'T HAVE IT.
- WHAT IS THAT NOISE?
ARE YOU ALIVE?
JENNI.
- WHAT?
- IT'S BREATHING
LIKE AN ALIEN.
IT'S BREATHING,
BUT REALLY WEIRD.
- LIKE...
[shallow breaths]
- NO, IT'S LIKE...
[hissing]
- IS YOURS DOING ANYTHING YET?
- JUST BREATHING.
- I MADE A BASSINET
FOR MINE.
- DUDE, MY BABY'S BORING.
THIS IS NOT A BABY
THAT I FEEL LIKE
I WOULD GIVE BIRTH TO.
- THESE BABIES ARE LIKE...
- CREEPY.
- THEY'RE CREEPY,
'CAUSE THEY JUST HAVE
NO FACIAL EXPRESSIONS.
THEY LOOK AT YOU LIKE
A LITTLE HAUNTED DOLL
FROM LIKE A HORROR MOVIE.
- OH, MY GOD.
ARE YOU AWAKE?
[doll crying]
OH, MY GOD!
- OH, MY GOD.
ARE YOU AWAKE?
[doll crying]
OH, MY GOD!
- IF YOURS IS ABOUT TO,
THEN MINE IS...
[doll crying]
- OKAY.
[both crying]
YOURS IS CRYING TOO?
- YEP.
'CAUSE YOURS WOKE MINE UP.
- MAYBE YOU'RE HUNGRY.
WANT SOME BREAST MILK?
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
[both dolls crying]
[Jenni murmuring]
- WHEN THE BABY STARTS CRYING,
YOU HAVE LESS THAN TWO MINUTES
TO FIGURE OUT
THE FOUR POSSIBILITIES
OF WHY IT'S CRYING--
WHETHER IT NEEDS TO BE
BURPED, ROCKED,
FED, OR DIAPER CHANGE.
[crying dies down]
- IT WAS A DIAPER!
[loud crying resumes]
OH, MAYBE NOT.
[dolls continue bawling]
I HAVE A DRAMA QUEEN.
IT'S NOT EVEN REAL.
I THINK THESE BABIES ARE HARDER
THAN I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE
TO TAKE CARE OF THEM.
[crying continues]
THEY'RE PRETTY MUCH A HANDFUL.
- EVERY TIME IT CRIES,
MY ADRENALINE
IS GOING HIGHER AND HIGHER.
- AND THE BABY'S REALLY HEAVY,
AND MY ARMS ARE LIKE KILLING ME.
[crying dies down]
MINE STOPPED.
GOOD LORENZO.
[dolls resume crying]
- OH, MY GOD.
[Snooki laughs]
OH! OH, NO!
- WAIT A MINUTE.
I HAVE TO TAKE THIS THING
TO THE GAY BAR TONIGHT?
- YEAH.
OH, [bleep].
SO TONIGHT
IS GAY JOEY PALOOZA,
AND I'M SO EXCITED
BECAUSE THE THREE JOEYS
ARE GONNA BE AMAZING.
[ding]
[dogs barking]
- YOU OR ME GETTING IT?
- I'M FEEDING.
- SO AM I!
- IT'S GONNA BE
A [bleep] SHOW.
- OH, HELLO.
[ding ding]
- JOEY.
- HI, JOEY. HOW ARE YOU?
[ding]
- HI.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD.
- WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- JOEY.
- I'M JOEY.
THIS IS THE GAY JOEY PARTY.
- YES, IT IS.
- WELCOME.
- WE'RE GONNA TRY AND SEE,
LIKE,
IF THE THREE JOEYS
CAN GET ALONG.
'CAUSE THIS IS
A VERY ODD DYNAMIC.
WE HAVE A TWINK...
- MORE PINK.
- AN OTTER...
- YOU LOOK LIKE
AN ALABAMA SLAMMER.
- AND A BEAR.
- WE'RE GONNA CUT HER OFF
REAL QUICK.
- SO WE HAVE THREE COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT DYNAMICS,
YET THEY'RE ALL
NAMED THE SAME.
- LET'S SKEDADDLE.
- SHOULD BE A GOOD TIME.
- WE'RE GOING TO THE GAY BAR!
- WE'RE BRINGING DOLLS
TO A BAR.
- MOVE IT, BITCHES.
- I WANNA SIT OVER HERE
WITH THE BABIES.
- WAIT.
IS THAT A REAL BABY?
- THAT'S MY BABY.
- WHERE'S LORENZO?
- AND THIS IS ISOBEL.
AND THIS IS JENNI.
THIS IS MY FRIEND BRANDON.
- HI.
- THAT'S CHRIS.
- JOEY.
- THIS IS MY FRIEND JOEY.
- THERE'S ANOTHER JOEY.
- THERE'S ANOTHER JOEY TOO.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- ORANGE AND CRANBERRY JUICE.
[doll crying]
- OH, NOW THEY [bleep]
WOKE UP.
- I WOULD NEVER TAKE MY REAL
BABY TO THE BAR, OBVIOUSLY.
BUT YOU KNOW, THIS REAL BABY,
IT'S EITHER
YOU LEAVE IT AT HOME
AND GIVE IT NEGLECT,
OR YOU TAKE IT TO THE BAR
AND YOU TAKE CARE OF IT.
- I'M GONNA BREAST FEED.
- HA HA!
- JUST COVER ME.
AW, THAT'S A GOOD BABY.
- AWW! SEE, THIS IS WHAT
I WANNA DO IN PUBLIC.
- I AM NOT STOPPING MY GAME
FOR THIS CHILD.
- IT'S GAY JOEY NIGHT.
- I JUST HAD A JOEY SANDWICH.
THERE'S NOTHING BETTER
THAN HANGING OUT
WITH YOUR GAY BEST FRIENDS
AT A GAY BAR
WITH TWO FAKE BABIES.
- WHERE'D YOU PUT
THE OTHER DIAPER?
- I'M OUT OF DIAPERS.
- WE ONLY HAD ONE DIAPER.
I BROUGHT IT WITH HIM.
- NO, I BROUGHT TWO.
WHAT'D YOU DO WITH IT?
- CHECK IN HIS PANTS.
- WHERE'S THE STROLLER?
- OVER HERE.
- CHECK THE RED DOLL STROLLER.
THE DIAPER'S MISSING.
LOOK, I DID NOT LOSE
THIS [bleep].
- YEAH, YOU DID.
- WE'RE MISSING
A [bleep] DIAPER.
- JOEY, OPEN YOUR EYES.
- YOU UNDERSTAND
THAT THE BABY CRIES.
- IT'S--OH!
- I PUT IT ON YOUR
[bleep] HEAD!
- SO RIGHT NOW IT'S JUST
A [bleep] SHOW,
'CAUSE EVERYONE'S SMASHED.
- LET'S GO.
- AND I JUST WANNA
GET MY BABY HOME,
AND I WANNA GO TO SLEEP
BECAUSE I'M SO EXHAUSTED
FROM TAKING CARE OF LORENZO.
- OW!
- [laughing]
PASS ME. PASS!
- OW!
- THE THREE JOEYS ARE PRETTY
[bleep] TRASHED RIGHT NOW.
OH, MY GOD...
[laughing]
MY JOEY'S PRETTY
[bleep] UP.
AND WHEN I FLIP THE COUCH
OVER TO [bleep] WITH HIM,
IN THE CREASE
IS HIS THROW UP.
YOU DID THROW UP!
JOEY, YOU THREW UP IN THE COUCH.
- AAH!
- AND HE THREW UP
ALL OVER THE PLACE,
AND NOW I WANNA THROW UP
BECAUSE OF IT.
- I DIDN'T THROW UP.
- HE NEEDS TO GET IT ALL OUT.
- NO!
- IT'S A GOOD NIGHT.
- [laughing]
SORRY.
- THERE'S MORE
SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW ON THE WAY,
AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
[doll fussing]
[crying]
- SO I'M PRETTY MUCH
BEING WOKEN UP
EVERY SINGLE HOUR
DURING THE NIGHT,
TRYING TO TAKE CARE
OF THE BABY.
THE BABY'S CRYING.
HE WANTS A BOTTLE.
HE NEEDS HIS DIAPER CHANGED.
AND I'M LIKE, HONESTLY,
I JUST WANNA THROW THE THING
AND BE LIKE, "SHUT UP,"
BECAUSE I LOVE MY SLEEP.
[crying quiets down]
BUT THEN AGAIN, I MEAN, THIS IS
REALLY GOING TO HAPPEN
IN LIKE SIX MONTHS,
SO I JUST BREATHE
AND I TAKE IT.
[doll crying]
DOES YOUR BABY
KEEP YOU UP ALL NIGHT?
- NO. NOT REALLY.
- MINE LIKE KEPT ME UP LIKE...
FOR THREE HOURS.
- YOU WASH YOUR VAGINA?
- HE'S NOT GOING UP THERE.
- DON'T YOU FEEL LIKE YOU
HAVE TO, THOUGH, JUST IN CASE?
- YEAH. THAT'S WHY
I TOOK A SHOWER.
- SO TODAY ME AND JENNI
ARE GOING TO MY APPOINTMENT
AND I'M VERY EXCITED,
BECAUSE I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
LITTLE SHRIMP AGAIN
ON THE MONITOR.
AND ALSO I'M GONNA ASK THE
DOCTOR IF HE CAN TELL THE SEX,
BECAUSE THAT WOULD BE
REALLY COOL.
[pop music]
[dogs barking]
- STOP!
HELLO! STOP.
[doll crying]
- * HOW DO WE FACE
THE BITTERNESS *
* NOW THAT THE SMOKE *
* HAS CLEARED *
[crying continues]
* WE'VE HAD OUR SHARE *
* OF DIFFERENCES *
* BUT I STILL NEED YOU HERE *
[doll bawling]
- I'M LATE
TO MY APPOINTMENT.
[crying continues]
I WANT IT TO WAKE UP AND CRY
WHEN JIONNI HOLDS IT.
I WANNA SEE
WHAT HE CAN DO.
- MOM!
- HI, MOM.
- YOU LOOK GREAT FOR
JUST HAVING A BABY.
- THIS IS LORENZO.
RIGHT WHEN I GET TO THE DOCTOR,
I SEE MY MOM WAITING
AND JIONNI.
HOLD LORENZO.
- UM, IT'S MORAL SUPPORT.
- I'M NOT KIDDING.
- WHOA, THAT'S PRETTY HEAVY!
- I KNOW, IT'S REAL!
- WHY'D YOU BRING
THIS THING HERE?
- 'CAUSE I NEED TO HOLD IT.
- SHE HAS TO.
- I CAN'T LEAVE IT AT HOME.
IT'S REAL.
IT'S REALLY NICE THAT,
YOU KNOW,
I HAVE THE SUPPORT
OF MY FAMILY.
[doll starts to cry]
TRY GIVING IT A BOTTLE.
[crying louder]
- HA HA.
- WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
- IT'S NOT WORKING.
- TRIGGER IT
ON THE BACK OF THE NECK.
- TRIGGER WHAT?
- THE THING IN YOUR HAND.
- PUT YOUR THING IN.
PUT IT IN THE BACK OF--
NO, YOU JUST PUNCHED IT!
- HA HA!
THIS ISN'T REAL.
- BUT PRETEND IT IS.
IT'S GONNA HAPPEN.
SO I'M TAKING THIS BABY
VERY SERIOUSLY,
AND JIONNI IS KIND OF NOT
AND, YOU KNOW, IT KINDA SUCKS.
IT'S LIKE A BUZZ KILL.
- I'M WORRYING ABOUT
MY REAL CHILD...
NOT THIS FRICKIN' THING.
- WHAT'S UP?
- HOW ARE YOU?
- HOW'S IT GOING?
- HI, DR. RUSSO.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
HOW YOU DOING?
ALL RIGHT.
SO HOW YOU FEELING?
- GOOD.
- GOOD?
WHY DON'T YOU LIE BACK?
OKAY.
SEE RIGHT OVER HERE,
THIS IS A THIGH BONE RIGHT HERE.
AND THIS IS ONE OF
THE SHIN BONES.
THE LEGS ARE KINDA FLEXED
RIGHT NOW.
THAT'S THE BABY'S HEAD
RIGHT THERE.
- AW.
- IT'S JUST SUCH A BIG HEAD.
COOL.
- ARE YOU HAPPY?
- I AM HAPPY.
- YOU CRYING?
- NO, I'M FINE.
- I WAS WATCHING
MOM'S EXPRESSION.
'CAUSE SHE WAS GONNA CRY,
I WAS ABOUT TO CRY.
- SO--
- [giggling]
- IF IT HAS--
IF IT HAS A WEINER?
- YEAH, CAN YOU SEE?
- CAN MAKE A GOOD GUESS.
IT LOOKS LIKE A BOY.
ALL RIGHT?
- A BOY!
IT'S A BOY.
- I KNEW IT.
AND I KNEW--
- JENNI CALLED IT.
- I KNEW THE DOCTOR
WAS GONNA SAY A BOY
BECAUSE YOU COULD SEE
THE PEE-PEE.
- THAT'S IT RIGHT THERE.
- THE WIENER?
- YEAH. I THINK SO.
- JIONNI GAVE HIM
A PRETTY DECENT PENIS.
- EEW! THAT'S MY SON!
- I CAN SAY YOUR SON
HAS A NICE PENIS.
- THAT'S [bleep]
DISGUSTING.
- I'M--I'LL SAY MY SON
HAS A NICE PENIS.
- UGH!
IT'S A BOY!
- IT'S A BOY.
- AND A BURP.
- NOW I KNOW WHAT COLOR
TO PAINT THE SPARE ROOM.
- IT ALL FEELS REAL NOW
BECAUSE I KNOW THE SEX
OF THE BABY.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS LIKE
THE REAL DEAL.
LIKE I AM HAVING
A BABY BOY.
NOW WE GOTTA PLAN
THE BABY SHOWER.
[doll cries]
- OH, COME ON, CHILD.
[doll crying]
- JENNI!
- MY BABY!
- I FEEL LIKE, YOU KNOW,
WE SHOULD SWAP BOYFRIENDS.
- I THINK
WE'LL NEED A DRINK FIRST.
- MIGHT AS WELL GET
TWO DRINKS.
- THE MORE PREGNANT I GET,
THE MORE I FEEL I SHOULD
REALLY BE EXPERIENCING THIS
WITH JIONNI
INSTEAD OF JENNI.
I KIND OF FEEL LIKE I NEED
TO BE WITH JIONNI.