[doorbell]
- POOP!
- HI.
HOW'S YOUR BABY?
- IT'S YOUR BABY.
- OH.
IT'S NOT A BABY.
I RESPECT
AND I THINK IT'S AWESOME
THAT SHE'S INTO IT LIKE THAT,
BUT...IT'S A DOLL.
YOU HUNGRY?
CAN I BUY YOU SOMETHING?
CAN I BUY YOU DINNER?
- WE'RE GOING TO DINNER
TONIGHT.
- OH.
- CAN YOU HOLD HIM REAL QUICK?
- COME ON.
- I HAVE TO GO TO THE BATHROOM.
I'M NOT KIDDING.
- OH, MY GOD.
- DON'T HOLD IT LIKE THAT!
[doll crying]
JIONNI!
- WHAT?
- YOU LEFT THE BABY CRYING?
- OH, HE'S CRYING?
- WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
YOUR FEET UP.
IT'S NOT FUNNY.
- YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO TAKE CARE
OF THE BABY.
- SO ARE YOU!
THE ONLY REASON
WHY I'M NOT MAD AT JIONNI
IS BECAUSE I KNOW,
WHEN WE HAVE OUR CHILD,
JIONNI IS GOING TO BE
THE GREATEST FATHER EVER.
HE'S GONNA CHOKE.
- HE'S EATING CARROTS
WITH HIS DAD.
- WHAT'S UP, BUDDY?
- WHAT'S UP, ROG?
- WHERE ARE WE GOING TO EAT
AND WHAT TIME?
- I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
BAR MAJESTIC
IS SUPPOSED TO BE COOL.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE
AN OLD THEATER.
- I'M VERY IMPRESSED
WITH YOUR GIRL.
- IT'S A DOLL, ROG.
- BUT YOUR GIRL'S
TAKING IT SERIOUSLY,
YOU SHOULD TAKE IT SERIOUSLY.
- OKAY, WELL, THIS IS MY KID.
CAN YOU HELP ME OUT?
- YOU'RE THE UNCLE.
- YEAH, I'LL HOLD THE KID.
- AW.
- IT'S NOT A PROBLEM.
NOT EVEN GONNA DRINK
WHILE I'M HOLDING THIS KID.
I FEEL LIKE I'M HOLDING JIONNI
WHEN HE'S DRUNK.
- BRO, YOU'RE DOING GOOD
WITH IT.
- I'M GONNA BE
A GREAT DAD, DUDE.
AS SOON AS I FIND
THE RIGHT WOMAN,
I'M GONNA BE A GREAT FATHER.
[laughs]
- SHE DIDN'T HEAR YA.
- ALL RIGHT, DO YOU WANT
YOUR BABY BACK?
- NOT YET.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN, "NOT YET"?
- YOU CAN GIVE IT BACK.
- I GAVE YOU A BREAK.
ASK ME IF I WANTED TO HOLD IT.
[doll screaming]
- JENNI!
- MY BABY!
- HOW'S IT FEEL?
SORRY ABOUT THE KID.
- I DON'T MIND ME.
- GIVE ME MY BABY.
[doll screams]
- IT'S QUIET.
- IT'S ROMANTIC.
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA GET?
- CHICKEN.
- WHAT ARE YOU GETTING?
- I WAS GONNA GET
WHAT YOU GOT, BUT--
- WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
YOU DON'T LIKE ANYTHING.
- I'M JUST A BITCH RIGHT NOW.
- SHE'S JOKING.
- SHOULD BE, UH--
- WE'RE GONNA HAVE FUN.
- NOT LIKE THIS, WE'RE NOT.
- YEAH, WE ARE.
- NICOLE, DO YOU WANNA TELL THEM
WHY WE BROUGHT 'EM HERE?
- THERE'S A KICKER
TO THIS DINNER?
- IS THERE A REAL REASON
WE'RE HERE?
- YES.
- WHAT IS IT?
- ME AND JENNI DECIDED...
- [pained sigh]
- THAT WE'RE GONNA MOVE OUT
OF THE HOUSE.
- TO WHERE?
- I WOULD LIKE TO MOVE IN
WITH YOU.
- ARE YOU GUYS SERIOUS?
YOU'RE MOVING BACK HOME?
- I WOULD LIKE TO MOVE
BACK HOME.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- JUST THE FACT THAT SHE'S
IN HER SECOND TRIMESTER
AND SHE WANTS TO--
- I NEED TO BE WITH YOU.
- AND OBVIOUSLY OUR RELATIONSHIP
ISN'T WORKING HERE.
- YOU WANT TO MOVE IN WITH ME?
- YES, I DO.
- JIONNI WAS LIKE,
"YES, OF COURSE."
- AND ROGER LOOKED LIKE
HE COULD'VE CARED
TWO [bleep] [bleep].
LIKE, WHATEVER.
- COOL.
- YO, I HAVE AN IDEA.
I'LL BUY YOU
ALL YOUR DRINKS TONIGHT--
ANYTHING YOU WANT--
IF YOU CAN EAT A TABLESPOON
OF CINNAMON.
YOU SWALLOW IT,
AND YOU WIN.
WILL YOU DO IT OR NO?
- I GUESS SO.
- COULD I GET A TABLESPOON
AND A LITTLE THING OF CINNAMON?
- OKAY.
- I'M BUILDING UP MY SALIVA.
- WHAT'S THAT?
PREPPING?
- YEP.
- THAT'S ACTUAL, REAL,
LEGIT CINNAMON? OKAY.
- AM I GONNA THROW UP
OR SOMETHING?
- NO.
- HOLD THIS,
DO NOT SPILL ANY.
YOU'RE SWALLOWING CINNAMON, BRO.
JUST CINNAMON.
- I GUESS YOU'RE GONNA BE
BUYING DRINKS.
- SWA--SWALLOW IT.
SWA--SWALLOW IT.
SWALLOW IT.
NO, YOU CAN'T DRINK.
- EW!
BABE!
- HE'S THROWING UP!
HE'S THROWING UP!
- HE'S AN IDIOT.
- HE'S SO CUTE.
[laughter]
- IS THIS A [bleep] BABY?
- I HOPE NICOLE TAKES THIS
ALL SERIOUS.
[doll crying]
- OH, MY GOD.
- WHY DON'T YOU LIE BACK?
- [burps]
TODAY IS MY APPOINTMENT,
AND I'M VERY EXCITED
BECAUSE I'M GONNA ASK THE DOCTOR
IF HE CAN TELL THE SEX.
CAN YOU SEE?
- IT LOOKS LIKE A BOY.
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT, I LOVE IT *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
[bird chirping]
[phone line trilling]
- HELLO.
- HI.
DO YOU HAVE PREGNANT CLASSES?
I HAVEN'T REALLY READ
MY PREGNANCY BOOK AT ALL.
I'D RATHER TALK
TO ACTUAL PREGNANT WOMEN
THAN ACTUALLY READING
BECAUSE IT'S JUST, YOU KNOW...
READING.
- ACTUALLY,
WE HAVE ONE TONIGHT.
IT'S AN INTRODUCTION
TO THE BIRTH PROCESS.
- WHAT TIME?
- 7:30 SHARP.
- UM, OKAY,
'CAUSE I'M PREGNANT.
- CONGRATULATIONS!
- THANKS.
UM, DO YOU HAVE HOMEWORK?
- NOT PER SE.
I MEAN, YOUR HOMEWORK
IS IN YOUR BELLY.
- HUH?
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT.
- OKAY.
- BYE.
- THANK YOU.
- OH!
SORRY.
WILL YOU GO TO A PREGNANT CLASS
WITH ME AT 7:30?
- MM-HMM.
- OKAY.
I'M VERY EXCITED TO BE
IN THIS BIRTHING CLASS
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE
I'M GONNA LEARN A LOT MORE
FROM PREGNANT WOMEN
THAN DOCTORS OR, YOU KNOW,
ANYBODY ELSE.
- MAYBE I'LL BRING THE DOGS.
- OH, DEAR.
AND BABIES?
HELLO.
- HI.
[indistinct chatter]
- I'M NICOLE.
- JENNI.
- I'M AN ALCOHOLIC.
[light laughter]
THAT'S WHAT IT FEELS LIKE.
- WELL, PEOPLE DON'T USUALLY
BRING THEIR BABIES TO THE CLASS,
BUT, YOU KNOW, IT'S OKAY.
- I'M PRACTICING.
- UM, OUR TOPIC TONIGHT
IS GOING TO BE
EXPLORING PREGNANCY
AND BIRTH MYTHS.
LET'S START OVER HERE.
- I'M NICOLE,
AND THIS IS MY FIRST CHILD.
UNEXPECTED,
BUT I'M VERY HAPPY.
SO I REALLY KNOW NOTHING
ABOUT WHAT'S GOING ON.
BUT I'M REALLY NERVOUS
ABOUT MY VAGINA RIPPING
TO MY ASS[bleep]
AND ALL THAT STUFF.
- OH, MY GOD.
- RIGHT?
YEAH.
- EVERYBODY'S WORRIED
ABOUT THAT.
WHEN WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
THIS DELICATE AREA--
OKAY, THAT'S NOT REALLY--
- IS THAT THE BUTT?
- THE ANAL SPHINCTER, YES.
SOMETIMES, A DOCTOR
WILL DO A CUT,
CALLED AN EPISIOTOMY.
- THAT REALLY SCARES ME
ABOUT GIVING BIRTH.
THAT [bleep] IS NASTY,
AND I'LL [bleep] THROW UP.
- THIS IS WHAT YOUR PELVIS
LOOKS LIKE.
AND THE BABY IS GOING TO HAVE
TO MAKE A JOURNEY,
AND THEN KIND OF TURNING
A LITTLE BIT IN ITS WAY.
- YOU'RE GONNA MAKE HER
NOT WANNA HAVE KIDS.
- I KNOW.
- SO THEN ONCE IT
EXITS THE PELVIS,
IT'S IN THE VAGINAL CANAL,
AND THE BABY
COMES OUT FULLY
WITHOUT HAVING INJURED YOU.
HOW LONG DO YOU THINK IT TAKES
FOR SOMEBODY TO GIVE BIRTH?
- I, TECHNICALLY, I THINK,
WAS IN LABOR FOR 17 HOURS.
- DOES IT FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE POOPING?
- YES, IT DOES.
THEY TRY TO TELL YOU
THAT IT DOESN'T
BECAUSE I THINK THEY DON'T
WANT THE ASSOCIATION
OF, LIKE,
"OH, IT'S A BEAUTIFUL BABY,"
NOT A CRAP.
BUT IT'S EXACTLY LIKE POOPING.
- YECH.
I LOVE POOPING.
I'M NOT AFRAID TO SAY
THAT I HAVE TO POOP.
SO AS LONG AS I DON'T POOP
ON MY BABY DURING PREGNANCY,
IT'S FINE.
- THANKS AGAIN FOR COMING.
- THANK YOU.
- YEAH, THANK YOU.
OVERALL, I DEFINITELY ENJOYED
THE BIRTHING CLASS.
RIGHT NOW,
JENNI'S NEVER GONNA HAVE KIDS.
- I FEEL LIKE IT POSTPONED ME
A FEW MORE YEARS.
- IT DID.
- NOW I GOTTA GO PICK UP
MY REAL CHILDREN.
- THE DOGS.
- YEAH.
[pop music]
- * ALL THAT I ASK *
* ALL THAT I,
ALL THAT I *
* ALL THAT I ASK *
- YOU'RE GONNA LOVE
MY CHICKEN TAPAS.
I MISS COOKING FOR ROGER.
- YOU KNOW WHAT'S COOL?
LIVING HERE, I GREW UP,
AND, LIKE, YOU LET LOOSE.
- I STILL FEEL LIKE ROGER'S,
LIKE, NOT HAPPY THAT I'M HERE.
- I MISS SLEEPING WITH JIONNI.
THE MORE PREGNANT I GET,
THE MORE I FEEL I SHOULD REALLY
BE EXPERIENCING THIS
WITH JIONNI INSTEAD OF JENNI.
- I REALLY CAN'T BELIEVE WE
MOVED IN TOGETHER, TO BE HONEST.
- I DON'T THINK
WE WERE THINKING.
- YEAH, WE DO THAT A LOT.
- WE WENT OFF INSTINCT.
- WE HAVE A HABIT
OF DOING THAT A LOT THOUGH.
- I NEVER THINK.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
- ME NEITHER.
- WHY DO YOU THINK
I'M PREGNANT?
SO, YOU KNOW, JUST RIGHT NOW,
I'M KINDA CONFUSED
AS TO WHAT I WANNA DO.
I DON'T KNOW.
I KINDA FEEL LIKE I NEED
TO BE WITH JIONNI.
I MEAN, WE'RE NEWLY ENGAGED,
AND I HAVEN'T REALLY
SEEN HIM AT ALL.
SO I THINK WE BOTH HAVE SOME
[bleep] WE NEED TO DEAL WITH.
- ARE YOU REALLY SERIOUS
ABOUT MOVING?
OR IS THIS JUST LIKE ANOTHER
CONVERSATION WE ALWAYS HAVE?
- MOVING OUT?
- MM-HMM.
- YEAH.
- LIKE, SOON?
- LIKE, SOON.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
THE GUYS ARE GONNA SAY
WHEN WE TELL THEM THAT WE DON'T
WANNA LIVE TOGETHER ANYMORE?
- WELL, THEY'RE EITHER
GONNA BE REALLY HAPPY
AND BE LIKE, "OH, YAY,
OUR GIRLS ARE COMING HOME,"
OR THEY'RE GONNA BE LIKE,
"OH, [bleep].
I KINDA LIKED BEING ALONE,"
BECAUSE THEY ARE GUYS.
- I'M AFRAID.
- ME TOO.
- I'M HURT.
SHE HURTS ME.
SHE DOES THESE THINGS
THAT I WOULD NEVER DO TO HER.
AND YOU JUST SEE IT--
KINDA ONE SIDE OF THIS
BECAUSE AFTER THAT PHONE
GETS HUNG UP,
THEN YOU SEE
YOUR BEST FRIEND GOING
AND LAY DOWN
AND START CRYING.
- YOU LOOK REALLY COOL TODAY.
- OH.
- YOU LOOK LIKE ME.
BUT BIGGER BOOBS.
YOU READY?
I FEEL LIKE I'M DRIVING...
- A MONSTER TRUCK?
- AN 18-WHEELER.
- SORRY FOR LAST NIGHT.
THE AWKWARDNESS.
- I THINK YOU NEED WORK.
- IT'S NOT WORK.
IT'S JUST, LIKE,
CUTTING THE BULL[bleep] OUT.
- I MEAN, THEY EITHER NEED
TO RESOLVE THEIR ISSUES,
OR THEY JUST NEED
TO LET IT GO.
- OR BREAK UP.
- THAT'S WHAT I MEANT
BY "LET GO."
- OH.
- IT'S NOT EVEN YOU
THAT NEEDS TO WORK ON,
IT'S HIM TOO.
AND I DON'T THINK HE KNOWS
- I NEED SOMEONE ELSE
TO SHOW, LIKE...
OUTSIDE PERSPECTIVE.
- I'LL [bleep] TELL HIM.
- SHOULD WE GO SEE HIM?
- I THINK WE SHOULD DO A DATE.
LIKE, I'LL CALL JIONNI
AND SAY, "LET'S DO A DATE.
MEET ME HERE."
AND THEN YOU DO THE SAME
FOR ROGER,
AND THEN WE'LL JUST SWITCH.
AND THEN, LIKE,
ANY QUESTIONS THAT YOU HAVE
THAT YOU WANT ME TO ASK HIM--
THEN YOU CAN DO
THE SAME WITH JIONNI
'CAUSE I HAVE QUESTIONS TOO.
- INTERVENTION/21 QUESTIONS?
- YEAH.
- I HOPE ROGER AGREES.
- AND THEN I'LL SHOW UP,
AND HE'LL BE LIKE, "COOL."
[both laugh]
[line trilling]
POOP?
- HEY, WHAT'S UP?
- NOTHING,
I WAS JUST CALLING
AND SEEING IF YOU WANTED
TO GO TO DINNER AT 9:30.
[line trilling]
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- I WOULD LIKE TO DO DINNER
WITH YOU ONE LAST TIME.
- MEET ME AT HARD GROVE CAFE.
- THERE'S THIS PLACE
CALLED MERCHANT.
- OKAY.
- OKAY, SO I'LL SEE YOU THERE
AT 9:30.
- ALL RIGHT, BABE.
SEE YOU AT 9:30.
- ALL RIGHT, LOVE YOU.
- OKAY, LOVE YOU.
[dial tone]
- [bleep].
IT'S ACTUALLY
A PRETTY GOOD PLAN.
- I'M GONNA BARBARA WALTERS
THAT [bleep].
- MM.
I LOVE BARBARA.
YOU LOOK LIKE BARBARA RIGHT NOW.
- THANKS.
GOOD LUCK WITH JIONNI.
- GOOD LUCK WITH ROGER.
- TELL HIM I LOVE HIM.
- I WILL.
- IF IT'S GOOD.
IF IT'S BAD,
TELL HIM TO [bleep] OFF.
[exciting music]
* *
- FEEL AWKWARD?
- WHAT'S UP?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I'M YOUR DATE TONIGHT.
- OH, YEAH?
- UGH.
SO I'M BASICALLY HERE...
- [clears throat]
- FOR NICOLE.
- OKAY.
- 'CAUSE I HAVE QUESTIONS.
- ALL RIGHT.
SHOULD I BE EXCITED
OR NERVOUS?
- BE EXCITED.
I WANNA GET TO KNOW YOU.
- ALL RIGHT.
UH-OH.
ARE THESE THE LIST OF QUESTIONS?
ASK AWAY.
- [chuckles]
I THINK WE'LL NEED
A DRINK FIRST.
- MIGHT AS WELL
GET TWO DRINKS.
- I'M A LITTLE NERVOUS
RIGHT NOW.
YOU KNOW, IT'S
A LITTLE NERVE-WRACKING
SEEING JENNI ACROSS THE TABLE.
SHE'S ABOUT 2 FEET
TALLER THAN ME.
AND, LIKE, THIS IS
THE FIRST TIME THAT JENNI AND I
ACTUALLY SAT DOWN AND TALKED
TO EACH OTHER LIKE THIS.
- HEY, ROG!
- OH! WHOA.
- I'M YOUR DATE.
- I WAS GONNA SAY,
LIKE, "WHAT'S GOING ON?"
WHERE'S JENNI?
ARE YOU JOINING US?
- NO, YOU'RE NOT HAVING
A BIG-BREASTED GIRLFRIEND
FOR DINNER.
[Roger laughing]
IT'S JUST ME.
- OH, REALLY?
THIS IS GONNA BE
INTERROGATION,
BUT I KINDA WELCOMED IT,
YOU KNOW,
'CAUSE IT'S A SIDE OF ME NICOLE
REALLY HAS NEVER GOT TO SEE.
- HOW COME YOU GUYS
FIGHT SO MUCH,
LIKE, OVER THE LITTLEST THINGS,
AND THEN IT TURNS OUT TO BE
FIGHTING ABOUT THE SAME [bleep]
OVER AND OVER?
- IT'S THE SAME COUPLE OF THINGS
THAT WE'VE FOUGHT ABOUT
FROM DAY ONE.
IT'S THE INSECURITIES
AND THE MISTRUST AND THE LYING.
IT'S REALLY
THOSE THREE THINGS.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
MAYBE SHE COULD BE A LITTLE
MORE OPEN TO [bleep] SEX.
BUT OTHER THAN THAT,
THAT'S IT.
- [giggling]
EW.
- DO YOU THINK THAT THE PROPOSAL
WAS SOONER THAN EXPECTED
BECAUSE NICOLE WAS PREGNANT?
- OF COURSE,
IT WAS DEFINITELY SOONER.
BUT YOU KNOW,
SHE'S GOING THROUGH A LOT--
HAVING A BABY.
I THOUGHT SHE'D BE
VERY COMFORTABLE
WITH A RING ON HER FINGER,
KNOWING THAT I'M GONNA BE THERE.
- I'M GLAD WE'RE HAVING
THIS DINNER
BECAUSE WHEN YOU GUYS
WERE FIGHTING,
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
JUST BEING SO MEAN TO HER.
- MM-HMM. I KNOW.
I'VE HEARD YOU SAY IT BEFORE.
"WHY DOES HE SAY THOSE THINGS?
WHY IS HE SO MEAN TO HER?"
AND I AM MEAN,
BUT THERE'S A REASON BEHIND IT.
I'M HURT.
SHE HURTS ME
BECAUSE SHE DOES THESE THINGS
THAT I WOULD NEVER DO TO HER.
AND YOU JUST SEE IT--
KINDA ONE SIDE OF THIS,
BECAUSE AFTER THAT PHONE
GETS HUNG UP,
THEN YOU SEE YOUR BEST FRIEND
GOING AND LAY DOWN
AND START CRYING.
BUT YOU'RE NOT SEEING THE HURT
AND THE PAIN THAT I FEEL.
- WHAT IF SHE WAS BROKE?
WHAT IF SHE WAS THREE YEARS AGO
WITH THE PIECE OF [bleep] CAR
THAT SHE HAD
AND NO MONEY, NOTHING?
HOW WOULD THAT BE?
- I DON'T HAVE
A PRIVATE LIFE ANYMORE.
IF I DIDN'T LOVE HER, IT WOULD
MAKE NO SENSE TO BE WITH HER.
MAKE NO SENSE.
MONEY'S NOT WORTH
WHAT I HAVE BEEN THROUGH.
- I THINK JIONNI HANDLED
HIS INTERROGATION RATHER WELL.
HE WAS HONEST 'CAUSE
HE COULD'VE BULL[bleep] ME.
AND TO BE HONEST, YOU KNOW,
I DO WORRY ABOUT THEM,
BUT I KNOW HE'S GONNA BE
A GOOD DAD.
[both laughing]
- IT WAS A GOOD TALK.
- DO YOU THINK JENNI'S
YOUR SOUL MATE?
- I WANT HER TO BE.
I DON'T WANNA BE WITH ANYBODY
ELSE ON THE FACE OF THIS PLANET.
I WANNA BE WITH JENNI.
I LOVE JENNI.
YOU KNOW?
- I DON'T SEE THE [bleep]
BIG DEAL RIGHT NOW.
SO GOING INTO THIS,
I'M OBVIOUSLY TEAM JENNI.
BUT THEN AFTER TALKING
WITH ROGER,
I FEEL LIKE I UNDERSTAND ROGER
ON WHY HE ACTS THE WAY HE ACTS.
THIS IS RETARDED.
LIKE, YOU GUYS ARE [bleep] UP.
- [laughing]
I KNOW.
- I KINDA WANNA YELL AT JENNI
A LITTLE BIT.
- DON'T DO THAT
'CAUSE SHE WILL FIGHT WITH YOU.
- NO, I'M NOT GONNA
YELL AT HER, NO.
IT'LL BE FINE,
HOPEFULLY.
- THERE'S MORE
SNOOKI AND JWOWW ON THE WAY,
AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
- BOO, I'M HOME.
- BOO, SOMEONE PEED.
- I'M NOT SURPRISED.
HOW WAS DINNER?
- HE HAD A LOT TO SAY.
- OH, NO.
I TOLD YOU.
- HOW WAS YOURS?
- WELL, BASICALLY, LIKE...
HE IS HAPPY
THAT HE'S ENGAGED.
BUT HE DID SAY
HE DEFINITELY PROPOSED TO YOU
WITH A YEAR SOONER
THAN INTENTIONALLY,
BUT HE WANTED TO DO IT
OUT OF RESPECT
FOR WHAT YOU'RE GOING THROUGH,
WHICH I THOUGHT WAS NICE.
- BUT HE WAS GONNA
DO IT ANYWAY.
- HE WOULD'VE DONE IT
WITHIN A YEAR.
- OKAY, SO IT'S NOT BAD.
- HE LOVES YOUR LIFESTYLE.
AND IF ALL THIS GOES AWAY,
HE WOULD FIND A WAY
TO SUPPORT HIS FAMILY.
- IT'S ALL GOOD.
- YEAH.
- EVERYTHING
THAT I WANTED TO HEAR I HEARD.
AND I KINDA KNEW ANYWAY.
SO HOPEFULLY ME AND JIONNI WILL
BE MADLY IN LOVE WITH EACH OTHER
AND HARDLY HAVE
ANY PROBLEMS,
YOU KNOW,
UNTIL THE DAY WE DIE.
- DOT, DOT, DOT.
I'M [bleep].
- IT WASN'T--NO.
NOT AT ALL.
HE'S [bleep]
SO IN LOVE WITH YOU.
IT'S ACTUALLY REALLY CUTE.
HE SAID HE'S WILLING
TO DO WHATEVER...
- REALLY?
- TO MAKE YOU GUYS WORK.
HE SAID HE'S DEFINITELY
GONNA WORK ON IT,
AND HE SAID YOU HAVE
TWO BIG THINGS TO WORK ON,
WHICH IS LYING
AND TRUSTING HIM.
BECAUSE HE SAID
IT REALLY HURTS HIM
BECAUSE HE CARES AND LOVES YOU
TOO MUCH TO LEAVE YOU.
- REALLY?
THAT'S ACTUALLY VERY SHOCKING.
I'M VERY HAPPY THAT ROGER'S
ACTUALLY DEDICATED
IN OUR RELATIONSHIP
AND WORKING ON OUR PROBLEMS
BECAUSE I THOUGHT HE WAS
ON THE VERGE OF GIVING UP.
AND TO HEAR
THAT HE DOESN'T WANT TO
MAKES ME FEEL GOOD.
- OH, POOP.
POOP, POOP, POOP.
- CAN I?
THINK I CAN FIT JUST
A LITTLE BIT MORE.
- SOMEONE'S EXCITED TO LEAVE.
[doorbell]
THAT'S ROGER.
- HI!
DO YOU WANNA COME HOME?
- YEAH.
- WHY CAN'T MY POOP
COME FIRST?
- AWESOME, YOU GUYS ARE
ALL PACKED, READY TO GO.
- I AT LEAST STARTED.
- THAT'S GOOD.
- I DIDN'T START!
- AWESOME.
[doorbell]
- [squeals]
- UH-OH.
THAT'S YOUR BOY BLUE.
- I AM VERY EXCITED
FOR NICOLE TO MOVE IN WITH ME.
YOU KNOW, I GET TO SEE HER,
I GET TO TAKE CARE OF HER.
YOU KNOW, THE WHOLE PREGNANCY,
I THINK SHE REALLY--
SHE REALLY NEEDS ME
TO BE BY HER SIDE.
- GO UPSTAIRS AND BRING
ALL MY LUGGAGES DOWN HERE.
CAN YOU PACK ALL MY SHOES
ON TOP?
- WHATEVER YOU WANT,
BABY.
- BOYFRIENDS ARE MANUAL LABOR.
I MEAN, THEY'RE CARRYING
THAT HEAVY [bleep]
DOWN THE STAIRS.
- YEAH, WE CAN'T DO
THAT [bleep].
- MM-MM.
- POOP, DON'T BRING
MY COMFORTER.
JUST MAKE MY BED.
- I GOTTA MAKE IT?
- JIONNI'S ACTUALLY HELPING.
I'M IMPRESSED.
DON'T DO THAT
WITHOUT A PROPER SPOT.
- ARE THOSE RED BOOTS YOURS?
- WE'RE NOT DOING BAD.
- WHOO!
- TAKE EVERYTHING FROM UPSTAIRS,
AND PUT IT DOWNSTAIRS.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO THROW IT IN
LIKE YOU'RE ANGRY.
- SHUT UP.
- I'M JUST A BITCH.
- THIS IS THE MOST WORK
YOU'VE DONE IN THREE YEARS.
- AT LEAST.
ALL RIGHT, BABE,
I'M GONNA GO.
- I'M OUT.
- BYE.
- THANK YOU, POOP.
- YOU'RE WELCOME.
- LOVE YOU.
WHY ARE YOU SO FAR AWAY?
- I'M GONNA FURTHER AWAY
IN A LITTLE BIT.
- I ACTUALLY REALLY
DON'T WANNA GO.
- WAIT, WHY ARE WE
LEAVING AGAIN?
- BECAUSE YOU NEED TO FIX
[bleep] WITH ROGER,
AND I'M PREGNANT.
[giggling]
- IT'S NOT LIKE
WE'RE DISAPPEARING
FROM EACH OTHER'S LIVES.
THAT'S MY GODCHILD IN THERE.
- I'LL SEE YOU ALL THE TIME.
- I KNOW.
I'LL PROBABLY COME AND SEE YOU
THIS WEEKEND.
- I'LL PROBABLY COME OVER
TOMORROW.
- SO WHO ARE WE KIDDING?
WE'RE GONNA CALL EACH OTHER
IN, LIKE, TWO HOURS.
- BYE.
IT FEELS BITTERSWEET
LEAVING JERSEY CITY.
- YEAH, WHO CAN SAY
THAT THEY LIVED IN A FIREHOUSE
AND TRANSITIONED IT
INTO, LIKE, GUIDETTE PALACE?
- MM-HMM.
AND I'M GONNA MOVE IN
TO JIONNI'S PARENTS' BASEMENT,
WHERE WE HAVE
A CUTE, LITTLE APARTMENT
AND, YOU KNOW, GET READY
FOR BABY LORENZO.
- AND I'M GONNA MOVE
BACK IN WITH ROGER DOWN SOUTH,
AND I'M GONNA FIX
MY RELATIONSHIP.
AND THEN AFTER, I'M GONNA
PROBABLY HAVE SEX WITH ROGER
TILL HE CAN'T HAVE SEX ANYMORE,
SO HE CAN SHUT THE [bleep] UP
ABOUT NOT HAVING SEX.
- THANK GOD!
ARE YOU CRYING?
- NO.
- YOUR EYES ARE WATERY.
YOU'RE CRYING!
- I'M NOT CRYING.
- YOU'RE CRYING.
- I'LL KICK YOU DOWN
THE [bleep] STAIRS.
- YOU'RE GONNA MISS ME.
- THAT'S EXACTLY WHY I'M MOVING.
- YOU'RE CRYING.
- I HATE YOU.
- NO, YOU DON'T THOUGH.
- WELL, BITCH,
I'LL BE SEEING YOU
BY THE BOTTOM OF MY FEET
AT THE SHORE.
- PREGNANT CITY AT SEASIDE.
- YEP.
AND I'M NOT HAVING
ANY OTHER ROOMMATE.
YOU'RE STUCK WITH ME FOR LIFE.
- * I AM PART OF YOU,
AND YOU ARE PART OF ME *
* A LINE OF ENERGY *
- I LOVE YOU.
I'M GONNA SEE YOU SOON.
- LOVE YOU.
- * DON'T QUESTION
YOUR WORTH *
- LOVE YOU!
- MISS YOU.
- I MISS YOU ALREADY.
DRIVE SAFE, BITCH.
I'M PREGNANT.
- I'M VERY HAPPY FOR YOU.
- WHAT'S THE OVER-UNDER
ON HIM BEING 5 FOOT?
- THERE'S A TURD
IN MY BEDROOM.
- SNOOKS?
- PAULY!
[girls scream]
I LOVE IT!
- AH!
- [yells]
[both scream]
- OH, MY GOD!
- JESUS!
- I [bleep].
WE'RE IN CANCUN!
[laughter]
IT WASN'T FUNNY.
NO ONE LAUGH.
[both laughing]
WHOO-HOO!
- THIS IS OUR SPECIAL MOMENT
TOGETHER. LET'S ENJOY IT.
- * WE'RE STARFRIENDS
ON EARTH *