- YOU'RE PREGNANT?
- HOLD ON ONE SECOND.
YOU'RE KNOCKED UP?
- AW, [bleep].
- IT'S NOT YOURS!
- WHEN YOU ARE PREGNANT,
YOU JUST WANT NOTHING
TO DO WITH SEX.
- OW!
- OH, SORRY.
BUT I'M ACTUALLY STARTING
TO GET MY SEX DRIVE BACK.
- I JUST WANT TO SNUGGLE.
- YET ANOTHER NIGHT FOR ME
OF NOT GETTING LAID.
OH, MY GOD.
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT, I LOVE IT *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
[guitar music]
* *
[jazzy music]
- I HAD A REALLY GOOD TIME
WITH JENNI LAST NIGHT,
AND I'M TRYING GET LUCKY
WITH MY GIRL,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I LOVE YOU.
[kisses]
JENNI'S NOT, LIKE,
A "LOVE-MAKING" TYPE OF GIRL,
BUT, YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE A NICE CHANGE
TO MAYBE, UH,
TAKE IT DOWN A NOTCH
AND KIND OF BE
A LITTLE MORE ROMANTIC
AND A LITTLE MORE PASSIONATE
ABOUT IT.
- BABE, STOP EXPOSING
MY [bleep], PLEASE.
- I WASN'T.
BABE.
[playful music]
BABY.
- ROGER'S SEX DRIVE
IS LIKE A 16-YEAR-OLD BOY.
- [kisses]
LET ME SLEEP.
- WHAT?
- I GOT NO [bleep] SLEEP.
- D'OH!
[rock music]
* *
- I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU GUYS
DIDN'T HAVE SEX.
- I KNOW.
SO, IF WE DO DINNER
AT 7:00 AND WE'RE BACK BY 10:00,
THEN WE CAN GO TO THE CLUB.
- I THINK SO.
- YOU DON'T CARE
TO GO TO THE CLUB
WITH THE BOYS
AND SOME FRIENDS?
- NO.
- 'CAUSE WE ONLY HAVE
SO MANY CLUB DAYS LEFT,
BUT I THINK--
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"CLUB DAYS LEFT"?
- I KNOW YOU'RE NOT GONNA GO
WHEN YOU'RE SHOWING.
- I JUST DON'T WANT TO GO
EVERY WEEKEND,
'CAUSE IT'S NOT FUN FOR ME.
YOU'D FEEL THE SAME WAY
IF YOU WERE PREGNANT, TRUST ME.
- WOW.
I'M DISAPPOINTED A LITTLE BIT
THAT NICOLE'S PULLING
THE PREGNANT CARD
A LOT MORE THAN I THOUGHT.
THIS IS SUPPOSED TO BE ME
AND NICOLE'S LAST HURRAH,
AND SHE'S NOT HURRAHING
AT ALL.
- I'VE BEEN TO THE CLUB
TWICE ALREADY, PREGNANT,
AND TRUST ME, I WANTED TO PUNCH
EVERYONE IN THE FACE.
ALL MY FRIENDS
WERE TAKING SHOTS.
EVERYONE'S
HAVING A GREAT TIME.
EVERYONE'S GETTING PLASTERED,
AND I CAN'T.
- JUST BECAUSE
YOU'RE PREGNANT
DOESN'T MEAN YOU DEVELOP A STICK
GOING THROUGH YOUR [bleep].
YOU CAN REMOVE THE STICK AND
SHAKE YOUR ASS A LITTLE BIT.
- I'M JUST WARNING YOU.
- IT'S THAT BAD?
- YEAH.
- I'M DOWN TO GO AND NOT DRINK.
I JUST WANT TO HEAR MUSIC
AND DANCE.
'CAUSE YOU AND JIONNI
CAN STILL DANCE.
- I DON'T KNOW MANY PREGNANT
WOMEN THAT GO TO THE CLUB.
- A LOT OF WOMEN
USE IT FOR CARDIO.
- I DON'T WANT TO BE
ONE OF THOSE.
[barks]
- SHH!
WHO'S THAT BOY THERE?
MY DOGS ARE, LIKE,
BARKING A LOT,
A LITTLE SPOILED
BECAUSE OF ME,
AND BECAUSE OF THAT,
THEY DO WHATEVER
THE [bleep] THEY WANT.
THAT'S NICE.
THAT'S REALLY NICE.
YOU GUYS DON'T EVEN AIM
FOR RUGS ANYMORE.
I WOULD LOVE
MORE THAN ANYTHING
FOR MY DOGS
TO BE POTTY-TRAINED.
ANOTHER BOOM.
OH, HE TOOK A NICE [bleep].
THAT'S GREAT.
I NEED THE [bleep]
DOG WHISPERER.
READY, BOO?
- WHERE ARE WE GOING?
- K9 GARDEN.
- ALL RIGHT.
- COME ON.
- * I'M BURNING RUBBER COMING
THROUGH YOUR BLOCK, BLOCK *
[dog barks]
- HEY.
- * NOBODY MESSING WITH MY FUMES
OR THE TOP, TOP *
- K9 GARDEN IS LIKE
A DOGGY DAYCARE.
[dogs barking]
- HELLO.
- * FOR THE SEEK
AND THE SPORT *
- WHO ARE THEY?
WHAT ARE THEIR NAMES?
- THE LITTLE ONE'S NOELLE,
AND THAT'S BELLA.
- HI, BELLA.
- DO YOU GUYS DO OBEDIENCE
OR ANYTHING?
- YES, WE DO.
[barking]
EVERY SINCE I MOVED HERE,
MY DOGS WON'T STOP--
- THEY PEE AND POOP EVERYWHERE.
- PEE AND POOP EVERYWHERE.
- YEAH, WE HAVE TRAINING.
WE HAVE--
WE HAVE GROOMING ALSO.
- I THINK IT'S A REALLY
GOOD IDEA,
BECAUSE BELLA'S A BITCH
AND SHE'S A DIVA,
AND I REALLY THINK
SHE SHOULD CHANGE.
AND NOELLE--NOELLE BARKS
AT EVERYTHING.
[barking]
SHE LOOKS BORED.
- SOMETIMES WE GET VOLUNTEERS
TO COME IN,
AND THEY HELP US WITH, LIKE,
THE SPECIAL NEEDS DOGS.
AND WE ACTUALLY HAVE
ADOPTION DOGS ALSO.
- I WENT TO SCHOOL
TO BE A VET TECH,
BUT I'M MORE OF
A CAT PERSON.
- OH, REALLY?
- SIT.
- YEAH, SMALL ANIMALS.
- OUR ADOPTION DOGS
ARE ALL SMALL ANIMALS,
SO IF YOU ARE INTERESTED
IN VOLUNTEERING,
WE COULD ALWAYS USE THE HELP.
- I WENT TO SCHOOL
TO BE A VET TECH,
AND I THINK IT WOULD BE
REALLY COOL
TO ACTUALLY VOLUNTEER
AT K9 GARDEN BECAUSE,
YOU KNOW, I NEVER REALLY DID
ANYTHING WITH MY SCHOOLING.
IF I WANTED TO VOLUNTEER,
WHERE DO I SIGN?
- RIGHT HERE.
- NICOLE DOESN'T WANT TO
PICK UP POOP,
AND SHE'S FREAKED OUT
BY BIG DOGS,
SO I DON'T KNOW WHY
SHE WANTS TO VOLUNTEER.
BUT, SHE WANTS TO DO IT,
SO SHE BETTER DO
A DAMN GOOD JOB,
'CAUSE I NEED THAT DISCOUNT.
YOU WON'T LOSE 'EM?
- I PROMISE YOU.
- JOEY'S INCREDIBLY GOOD
WITH DOGS.
- YOU'RE A JOEY?
MY BEST FRIEND'S JOEY.
- WE ALL--WE ALL NEED
A GAY JOEY.
- AAH! ISN'T THAT--?
- I'VE GOT ONE, YOU'VE GOT ONE.
- SHE HAS ONE TOO!
- I HAVE ONE TOO.
MAYBE ALL THE JOEYS
IN THE TRISTATE AREA ARE GAY,
AND THAT'S AWESOME.
- BYE. NO, PEANUT.
- AW!
- BYE, GUYS,
SEE YOU LATER.
- SEE YOU
IN A LITTLE WHILE.
- THANK YOU.
I WILL BE BACK.
[upbeat music]
* *
- SO, WHEN'D YOU HAVE
YOUR FIRST BOYFRIEND?
- UH, IT WAS CAMP.
IT WAS INNOCENT.
I WAS, LIKE, 10 OR 11.
I DON'T EVEN THINK
WE KISSED.
- WHEN'S THE FIRST TIME
YOU MADE OUT?
- I CAN'T REMEMBER.
- HOW DO YOU NOT
REMEMBER THAT?
- I REMEMBER TAKING
SOMEONE'S VIRGINITY.
THAT WAS FUN.
- OH, ME TOO.
- WE ENDED UP BEING TOGETHER
FOR, LIKE,
FOUR YEARS AFTER THAT.
- CHEAT ON HIM?
- I CHEATED ON HIM
WITH HIS BEST FRIEND.
- THE GUY THAT I WAS WITH
FOR FOUR--FOR FIVE YEARS,
I [bleep] HIS BROTHER.
[laughter]
WE WERE HORRIBLE.
- HOW'D THIS [bleep] HAPPEN?
- WE'RE LEGIT TWINS.
- YEAH, I KNOW WE ARE.
[laughs]
- I HOPE MY KIDS
AREN'T LIKE THAT.
- [laughs]
- I NEVER CHEATED
ON THE EX OR JIONNI.
[playful music]
VINNY, I DON'T CONSIDER,
'CAUSE I BROKE UP WITH HIM.
I SAID GOOD-BYE.
- GOOD-BYE. FFTT!
[laughter]
- I'LL NEVER DO THAT
EVER AGAIN.
- READY?
- YEAH.
BYE. THANK YOU.
- [laughs]
- SEE YOU SOON.
- THAT LADY PROBABLY THINKS
WE'RE SUCH WHORES.
- OH, YEAH.
- DO YOU THINK IT'S FAIR THAT
YOU JUST CONSTANTLY [bleep] ME?
YOU'RE BEING SUED RIGHT NOW.
- I AM?
- JUST DON'T LIE.
JUST DON'T LIE.
IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
- WHAT IS GOING ON
RIGHT NOW?
- * I SAW A REFLECTION
ON THE CORNER *
[dogs barking]
- HEY!
- * THE LIVING ROOM *
- SHH!
NICOLE, GET YOUR ASS UP!
[dogs barking]
MORNIN'.
YOU GOT TO VOLUNTEER.
- I KNOW.
- OKAY.
* *
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
YOU GOT YOUR PERIOD?
OH, WAIT.
- THAT WASN'T FUNNY.
NO ONE LAUGHED.
- I NEVER MET SOMEONE PREGNANT
AND SO TIRED.
- [groans]
- I'M SCARED FOR THE FUTURE,
BECAUSE IF NICOLE IS ACTING LIKE
THIS IN HER FIRST TRIMESTER,
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN
IN THE NEXT TWO?
- WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
- AT THE BEST IDEA EVER.
- WHAT?
- I WANT TO LEARN
HOW TO COOK.
BASICALLY, LEARN
HOW TO COOK ORGANIC.
- ORGANIC?
- YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I LOVE.
- LIKE GROSS FOOD?
- YEAH, GROSS FOOD.
- YOU EAT WEIRD FOOD.
- NO, I EAT REAL FOOD.
- WEIRD.
YOU EAT [bleep] PRUNES.
- I'M A GOOD COOK, BUT I DON'T
COOK OUTSIDE THE BOX.
- HAVE FUN WITH YOUR PRUNES,
OLD LADY.
- I WILL.
I WANT TO, LIKE,
LEARN HOW TO DO IT
WITHOUT, YOU KNOW,
GOOGLING IT.
YOU'RE, LIKE,
A HALF AN HOUR LATE.
- IT'S NOT A JOB.
IT'S VOLUNTEER.
- [under her breath]
SO WHINY.
- [muttering]
- I'LL BE IN THE CAR.
- WHAT THE [bleep]?
- [under her breath]
SUCH A BITCH.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME?
[laughter]
- * OH, GIVE ME
WHAT I WANT *
- I'M VOLUNTEERING TODAY.
- OUR GROOMER'S GONNA BE IN
AT ABOUT NOON,
SO YOU'LL BE WORKING WITH HER
TO HELP OUT,
LIKE, LEARNING HOW
TO DO THE BATHS.
THIS IS FOR YOU,
TO PROTECT YOU.
- DO I HAVE TO WEAR A HOODIE?
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO WEAR
A HOODIE.
- WHAT IF I GET SWEATY?
- WEAR THE HAT.
- SEE YOU LATER.
- BYE. BYE, I LOVE YOU.
HAVE FUN.
- OKAY.
[dogs barking]
- ALL RIGHT, YOU READY?
- YEAH.
[barking]
- SO, THE BEST WAY
TO COME ON THE FIELD
IS TO SLIDE IN SIDEWAYS,
JUST LIKE YOU DID,
AND CLOSE IT BEHIND YOU.
- NOW WHAT?
- NOW YOU JUST
PLAY WITH THEM.
- THIS IS YOUR JOB?
- I'M GONNA BRING
SOME MORE IN.
- IT'S THE EASIEST JOB
EVER.
- [laughs]
[dogs barking]
- OH, MY GOD.
THERE'S JUMPERS.
AAH!
[laughs]
OH, MY GOD,
HE'S JUMPING.
- I WON'T GET YOU
ANY JUMPERS.
- HELLO. WAAH!
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S CLAWING MY [bleep].
JEEZ!
IT'S BITING!
- COME ON, LOUIE.
- EW, SERIOUSLY,
I DON'T PLAY THAT GAME.
- COME HERE, LOUIE.
GO GET HER, LOUIE.
- AAH!
[dogs barking]
AAH!
THEY'RE PROTECTING ME.
I NEVER REALLY KNEW
THAT BELLA LOVED ME,
BECAUSE SHE BIT ME IN THE FACE
WHEN I TRIED TO GIVE HER A KISS,
AND I'M--I'M [bleep]
SCARED OF HER EVER SINCE.
IT IS JUMPY.
[dogs barking]
BUT NOW, LIKE,
ME AND BELLA ARE BONDING,
I FEEL LIKE BELLA'S
STICKING UP FOR ME,
LIKE, "GET AWAY
FROM MY FRIEND."
GO, GIRL.
BELLA IS, YOU KNOW,
MY BITCH.
- LOOKS LIKE WE HAVE
OUR FIRST POOP OVER THERE.
- [gags]
EW, IT'S FRESH.
[retches]
OH, GOD.
[hip-hop music]
* *
- ARE YOU IN HERE?
- HELLO.
- HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
- FINE. I JUST WOKE UP.
- SO, WHAT WOULD YOU
LIKE TO DO TODAY,
SINCE IT'S SO PRETTY OUT.
- NAILS. I'D BE
A VERY HAPPY PERSON.
- THAT'S THE OTHER THING
I HAVE TO DO.
I HAVE TO CALL THAT SALON.
AND THEN, I'M GONNA RUN
TO COOKING CLASS, COME BACK,
AND THEN I'M GONNA GO HAVE
AN AMAZING NIGHT AT POWERHOUSE.
- MM-HMM.
- DOES THAT SOUND GOOD?
- [belches]
- * I OPENED MY EYES *
* CRAWLED OUT OF BED *
* THAT'S WHEN I KNEW
STRANGE DAYS AHEAD *
- HI.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- CAN I MAKE A RESERVATION?
- UH-HUH.
- SO TONIGHT, I WANT TO GO
TO POWERHOUSE
AND CHECK IT OUT.
I HEARD THEY HAVE
REALLY GOOD MUSIC
AND WE'VE BEEN BUSTING OUR ASS
AND, LIKE, DOING THIS HOUSE
AND GETTING EVERYTHING DONE,
THAT WE HAVEN'T
TOOK OUT TIME TO ENJOY.
DO YOU HAVE ANY KIDS?
- I HAVE ONE SON,
14 YEARS OLD.
- DID IT HURT?
- HMM? WHAT'S THAT?
- DID IT HURT
TO PUSH OUT A BABY?
- YEAH, IT WAS BAD, YEAH.
ALMOST TOOK 20 HOURS OF PAIN.
- SHE'S KNOCKED UP.
- STOP SAYING IT LIKE THAT.
IT REALLY HURTS MY FEELINGS.
- REALLY?
- YEAH.
- WELL, IT'S TOO WEIRD
TO SAY THE "P" WORD.
- PREGNANT.
- IT'S
TOO CREEPY TO SAY THAT.
- IT'S NOT CREEPY.
I'M PREGNANT.
HOW IS--WHAT ELSE
DO YOU SAY?
- I MAKE A STUPID COMMENT.
- IT HURTS MY FEELINGS.
I'M VERY SENSITIVE.
- OH, MY GOD.
IF THIS IS WHAT
I HAVE TO DEAL WITH--
- YEAH. WAIT TILL
YOU GET PREGNANT.
- CALM DOWN, HORMONAL.
- NO.
- GOD, YOU TAKE
THIS [bleep] TOO SERIOUS.
[upbeat music]
* *
PUT YOUR BLINKERS ON
BEFORE I FIND IT.
- RIGHT HERE?
- YEP.
AND I'LL RUN IN
AND GET 'EM.
SO I'M HAULING ASS BECAUSE
WE ARE RUNNING BEHIND.
- SEE YOU TOMORROW.
- AND I'M GONNA SEE WHAT THIS
COOKING CLASS IS ALL ABOUT.
BYE, LADIES.
SEE YOU IN A LITTLE BIT.
- BYE, MOMMY.
- I'M ALREADY LATE.
- ALL RIGHT, GIRLS,
LET'S HEAD HOME.
- HI.
all: HI.
- WELL, WELCOME TO MADE WITH
LOVE ARTISAN BAKERY AND CAFE.
WHAT WE HAVE HERE
IS WHAT I CONSIDER TO BE
SIMPLE CUPCAKES THAT I THINK
EVERYBODY CAN MAKE.
YOU TAKE YOUR 65%
OR YOUR 70% CHOCOLATE.
YOU MELT IT,
YOU POUR HEAVY CREAM IN IT,
AND YOU WHISK IT, AND YOU
MAKE A CHOCOLATE GANACHE.
- GOES RIGHT TO MY ASS.
- THAT'S WHAT WE SERVE
AT THE, UH--
[laughs]
TAKE YOUR SPATULA OUT.
PUT YOUR SUGAR IN.
- WAIT, I CAN PUT ALL OF IT,
RIGHT?
- [belches]
OOPS.
[laughter]
- OKAY.
- PEOPLE JUST HAVE TO
GET USED TO ME.
SORRY.
- OKAY, WE CAN MIX.
- WHY ARE YOU BAKING?
DO YOU HAVE
SOMEONE TO IMPRESS?
- UH, YEAH, I DO,
ACTUALLY.
- OKAY, MORE MILK.
- REALLY?
- MY BOYFRIEND, HIS PARENTS
ARE PROFESSIONAL BAKERS.
- UHH!
WHAT A BURDEN.
MY PARTNER'S NAME IS ASHLEY,
AND SHE'S ACTUALLY REALLY COOL.
LIKE, SHE'S COMPLETELY DIFFERENT
FROM ME AND NICOLE,
BUT SHE HAS A VERY SWEET SIDE
TO HER,
AND I COULD
JUST RELATE TO HER.
- WHOOP.
- [laughs]
- FLYING SPATULA.
- IT TOOK OFF.
- OKAY.
- I'M INTERESTED IN GOING TO,
UH, POWERHOUSE.
- IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE
REALLY COOL.
- WANT TO COME?
- YEAH.
- YEAH?
- I'LL GO.
- NICOLE HAS BEEN A BITCH
TO ME LATELY.
IF SHE WANTS TO SIT AROUND
AND BE MISERABLE,
SIT AROUND AND BE MISERABLE.
I'M NOT GONNA SIT AROUND
AND BE MISERABLE WITH YOU.
GOOD NIGHT. THANK YOU.
BYE.
[upbeat music]
- * YOU CAN'T ALWAYS
HAVE EVERYTHING *
- YOU IN?
- HI.
HOW WAS COOKING CLASS?
- I MADE A FRIEND.
- A FRIEND?
- I INVITED HER.
- COOL.
- YOU'RE GONNA LIKE HER.
ASHLEY.
- WHY ARE YOU INVITING
THE WHOLE WORLD?
I JUST WANT TO GO TO DINNER
WITH YOU.
[playful music]
HOW ARE WE GETTING THERE?
- TAKE A CAB.
- YOUR NEW FRIEND'S
NOT PICKING US UP?
- [bleep] ME. WHY ARE YOU
SUCH A HATER?
- WHY ARE YOU SO SCARED
OF DINNER WITH ME ALONE?
I WASN'T SURE WE WERE
INVITING FRIENDS.
I WOULD HAVE INVITED FRIENDS.
- WHAT FRIENDS DO YOU HAVE
OUT HERE?
'CAUSE I HAVE NONE.
- I WOULD HAVE MADE ONE
ON THE STREET
WHEN YOU WERE GONE.
- I MEAN, IT'S REALLY
NOT MY FAULT THAT I MET SOMEONE
THAT'S A GENUINELY
NICE PERSON,
AND I'M SURE NICOLE
WILL GET OVER IT.
- JENNI, CABS ARE HERE.
[upbeat music]
* *
- DRINK YOUR PELLIGRINO.
- NO, I HAD TOO MUCH
CARBS TODAY.
- [laughs]
CARBONATED.
[laughter]
* *
I WANT TO FEEL LIKE
I'M ON A TROPICAL ISLAND.
- YOU WANT ME TO PUT THIS DOWN
OVER HERE?
- YEAH!
HI!
- IS THAT YOUR FRIEND?
- THIS IS NICOLE.
- HI.
- SHE'S MAD.
- WHAT? I'M NOT MAD.
I DON'T WANT TO MAKE JENNI
MY BITCH,
BUT I WANT HER TO
WANT TO HANG OUT WITH ME
INSTEAD OF INVITING STRANGERS.
- HER MAN'S FROM AUSTRIA.
- YEAH, HE'S FOREIGN.
- NICE.
- WE'RE GONNA MAKE HIM
TRY AND PROPOSE TO HER.
SHE JUST GOT PROPOSED.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
CONGRATULATIONS.
- THANKS.
- THAT'S A BEAUTIFUL RING.
- YES, IT'S RIDICULOUS.
- SHE'S ACTUALLY A REALLY,
REALLY NICE CHICK,
UM, BUT, YOU KNOW, I'M STILL
GIVING JENNI [bleep]
BECAUSE I LIKE TO BUST
HER BALLS.
- SO, THIS IS YOUR FIRST NIGHT
OUT? IN THE BIG JC?
- ISH.
- I WOULDN'T CONSIDER IT
THE FIRST NIGHT OUT.
- WE HAVEN'T BEEN TO A CLUB.
- YEAH, WE HAVEN'T BEEN
TO A CLUB.
- WELL, THERE'S, LIKE,
NONE AROUND HERE.
THAT'S PROBABLY
YOUR PROBLEM.
- THAT GUY TO YOUR LEFT
HAS BEEN CREEPING ME OUT.
- WHOA!
[laughter]
EMBARRASSING.
- OH, MY GOD, HE'S STARING.
ASHLEY, TAKE A LOOK.
- I CAN'T.
I DON'T WANT TO, REALLY.
[overlapping chatter]
- WHAT DID THAT GUY
SAY TO YOU?
- HE SAID,
HE WOULD LIKE TO KNOW
IF HE COULD BUY YOU GUYS
A DRINK?
- NO.
EW!
IF THIS GUY
BUYS US DRINKS,
HE COULD PROBABLY
SLIP US ROOFIES,
AND I'M PREGNANT, AND I
DON'T DO THAT ANYMORE.
WELL, NOT LIKE
I EVER DID THAT,
BUT THAT'S GROSS.
DO YOU WANT SOMETHING?
YOU'VE BEEN STARING AT US
FOR AN HOUR.
- NOT STARING.
- IT'S AWKWARD.
YOU'VE BEEN LIKE THIS
THE WHOLE TIME.
- STOP IT.
- YOU'RE CREEPING US OUT.
- REALLY?
- SO CREEPY.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
I'M SCARED OF
THE CREEPY PEOPLE,
BUT I'M NOT SCARED,
BECAUSE I HAVE JENNI.
- THANKS.
- AND JENNI WOULD
[bleep] KILL HIM, SO--
YOU WOULD KILL HIM.
- IF I HAD TO, YEAH.
- YEAH, SO--
- I'D STAB HIM IN THE EYE.
- I GOT MY BODYGUARD. [laughs]
- IF HE'S OUTSIDE OF
OUR HOUSE WHEN WE GET THERE--
- I FEEL LIKE HE'S GONNA
GRAB ONTO OUR BUMPER
AND COME WITH US.
- HE PROBABLY COULD SKATE
ON THAT THING.
- GOD. GO FAST.
WE HAVE A STALKER.
[laughter]
- THERE'S MORE
SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW ON THE WAY,
AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
[upbeat music]
[phone rings]
* *
[ringing]
- HOW ARE YA?
- UM, DO YOU HAVE
A LITTLE TIME?
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH, I'M OKAY.
UH, I DON'T KNOW
IF WE'RE OKAY, BUT--
- WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
- UM, LISTEN, I--I DON'T EVEN
KNOW HOW TO GO ABOUT THIS.
UH, I JUST HEARD SOME STUFF,
YOU KNOW,
ON THE RADIO THIS MORNING,
AND THEN I CALLED YOUR DAD
AND GOT COMPLETELY [bleep]
AND LIED TO BY HIM.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- OKAY, ARE YOU GONNA CONTINUE
TO LIE TO ME, OR--?
- NO, I'M NOT.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT RIGHT NOW.
- YET AGAIN,
YOU'RE LYING TO ME.
- I'M NOT LYING, ROGER.
WHAT ARE YOU TAL--?
I CALLED YOU--
- ALL YOU DO
IS LIE TO ME, JENNI.
THAT'S ALL YOU DO IS LIE TO ME.
- NO, I DON'T.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT THIS IS ABOUT.
- YOU'RE BEING SUED
RIGHT NOW,
AND I LEARN ABOUT IT
ON THE [bleep] RADIO?
- WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
I'M BEING SUED RIGHT NOW?
- IT'S ALL OVER THE NEWS.
I'M HEARING ABOUT IT
FROM EVERYBODY.
THIS IS
HOW I LEARNED ABOUT IT,
'CAUSE MY GIRLFRIEND
JUST LIES TO ME FOR YEARS NOW.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING--
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW ANY OF THIS.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHY ROGER'S
ACTING THE WAY THAT HE IS,
AND I HAD NO IDEA I HAVE
A LAWSUIT AGAINST ME RIGHT NOW
THAT HE KNOWS MORE ABOUT
THAN I DO.
- I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH CLEARER
I CAN PUT IT.
I KNEW YOU WERE EITHER GONNA GO
THE VICTIM ROUTE,
WHICH YOU LOVE TO DO.
- I'M NOT GOING
THE VICTIM ROUTE.
TO BE HONEST,
I'M A LITTLE SIDESTEPPED,
BECAUSE I HONESTLY THOUGHT,
LIKE,
YOU THOUGHT I CHEATED ON YOU
OR YOU CHEATED ON ME.
LIKE, THAT'S HOW THE [bleep]
CONVERSATION GOT STARTED.
- NO, IT'S ABOUT LYING IS WHAT
THIS IS ABOUT, ONCE AGAIN,
AND YOU CLAIM THAT
I NEED TO GET OVER--
- NO!
- I NEED TO GET OVER THE PAST
BECAUSE YOU'RE A NEW PERSON,
AND ALL THOSE LIES
THAT YOU USED TO TELL ME
IS NO LONGER YOU.
AND UNLIKE YOU,
I NEVER LIE.
I NEVER LIED TO YOU ONCE,
EVER.
- ROGER'S MAD AT THE FACT
THAT I LIE.
I LIE ABOUT STUPID [bleep]
ALL THE TIME,
BUT I LOOK AT, LIKE,
STUPID LIES AND, LIKE, BIG LIES.
LIKE, I FEEL LIKE THIS
IS A STUPID LIE
THAT HE'S TAKING
WAY TOO FAR.
- FOR ONCE IN YOUR [bleep]DAMN
LIFE, STOP LYING!
- MM-MM.
- DO YOU THINK THIS IS
A FAIR RELATIONSHIP, JENNI?
- IT IS FAIR, BUT ROGER,
I JUST WOKE UP.
- WAIT A MINUTE, YOU LET ME
FINISH.
YOU LET ME FINISH.
YOU THINK THIS IS
A FAIR RELATIONSHIP
THAT I AM NOTHING BUT BRUTALLY,
BRUTALLY HONEST WITH YOU?
NOT ONLY THAT,
I'VE LIVED THROUGH HELL
WITH, YOU KNOW,
ACCUSATIONS
AND EVERYTHING ELSE WITH YOU,
PROVED THEM ALL WRONG.
I'VE ALWAYS COME OUT
ON TOP.
- TRUST IS DEFINITELY THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING TO ROGER
AND NOT LYING,
SO HE [bleep] UP
BY DATING ME.
- DO YOU THINK IT'S FAIR THAT
YOU JUST CONSTANTLY [bleep] ME
AND LIE TO ME?
- I DON'T [bleep]
AND LIE TO YOU, ROGER.
- ALL YOU DO IS LIE.
- NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU LISTEN TO ME.
STOP!
SHUT UP FOR
FIVE [bleep] SECONDS!
- CALM DOWN!
- JESUS [bleep]!
YOU'RE REALLY [bleep]
PISSING ME OFF RIGHT NOW!
I SHOULDN'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT THIS!
I SHOULD HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT THE [bleep] LAWSUIT!
- YOU COULD DEFEND YOURSELF
BY TELLING ME
THAT YOU [bleep] LIED TO ME.
- I'M TELLING YOU
THE [bleep] TRUTH!
- WOW.
WOW.
JUST DON'T LIE.
IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
DON'T LIE.
ESPECIALLY TO SOMEBODY
YOU LOVE.
- I DON'T KNOW NOW.
I DON'T KNOW, I DON'T KNOW.
- JENNI, I CAN'T LIVE WITH THIS
[bleep] LYING ANYMORE.
- NO.
I AM [bleep], LIKE,
COMPLETELY...
[groans]
- I CAN GIVE YOU ALL
THE FACE TIME YOU NEED.
- WHAT IS GOING ON RIGHT NOW?
- IS HE COMING?
- I DON'T KNOW.
HE SAID HE IS.
I DON'T CARE.
ACTUALLY, I DON'T
WANT HIM TO COME.
[door slams and locks]
- HAVING A BABY IS GONNA BE
THE MOST LIFE-ALTERING
EXPERIENCE YOU'VE EVER HAD.
- I'VE GOT GREAT EXPERIENCE.
THREE OF MY SIBLINGS
HAVE BABIES.
- I DON'T THINK
THAT MEANS THAT YOU KNOW
EVERYTHING THERE IS TO KNOW
ABOUT CHILD-REARING.
- TRUST ME, I DO.
- THAT'S AN EXTREMELY
NAIVE STATEMENT.