- SHE'S KNOCKED UP.
- STOP SAYING IT LIKE THAT.
IT REALLY HURTS MY FEELINGS.
- REALLY?
- IT HURTS MY FEELINGS.
I'M VERY SENSITIVE.
- OH, MY GOD.
CALM DOWN, HORMONAL.
- DO YOU THINK IT'S FAIR
THAT YOU JUST
CONSTANTLY BULL-[bleep] ME.
YOU'RE BEING SUED RIGHT NOW.
JUST DON'T LIE.
IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
- WHAT IS GOING ON RIGHT NOW?
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT, I LOVE IT *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
- ALL THE PROBLEMS
WE'VE HAD IN THE PAST
WOULD BE COMPLETELY AVOIDED AND
AVERTED IF YOU WERE JUST HONEST.
- SORRY I LIED, ALL RIGHT?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT ELSE TO SAY.
I WAKE UP THIS MORNING,
AND I FIND OUT
THERE'S A LAWSUIT GOING
ON IN SOME WAY.
YEAH, I DID [bleep] UP, AND
I DIDN'T TELL HIM EVERYTHING,
SO I APOLOGIZED TO HIM.
AND I AM SORRY FOR THAT.
- YOU KNOW WHAT WE'VE BEEN
THROUGH IN THE PAST.
I WOULD THINK THAT,
FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, YOU KNOW,
WOULD YOU STOP WITH
THE BULL-[bleep] ALREADY,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- I WAS 22 YEARS OLD!
- IT IS WHAT IT IS, YOU KNOW?
- MM.
- I COULD HAVE CARED LESS
IF SHE WAS BEING SUED.
WHY WOULD THAT MAKE
ANY DIFFERENCE TO ME?
I DON'T CARE.
IT'S THE MISREPRESENTATION
OF YOURSELF
AND THE LYING,
THAT BOTHERS ME.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, CALL ME LATER
AND WE'LL TALK, I GUESS.
- OKAY.
BYE.
I AM [bleep] SO PISSED
OFF RIGHT NOW.
I'M, LIKE, READY
TO THROW UP RIGHT NOW.
- YOU NEED A COCKTAIL.
- I NEED TO GET OUT
OF THIS HOUSE.
- CAN I HAVE
A TOASTED BLUEBERRY MUFFIN?
I HOPE HE COMES TONIGHT.
- HE FLAKES OUT ON ME
ALL THE TIME,
AND WE FIGHT.
THE PLAN TONIGHT
IS LUCKY CHENG'S,
A RESTAURANT IN NEW YORK CITY
THAT OFFERS
A DRAG SHOW DURING IT.
BUT, I FEEL LIKE
I CAN ALMOST GUARANTEE
THAT TONIGHT'S
GONNA BE A BUST,
BECAUSE
OF ME AND ROGER'S FIGHT.
- MM, THAT WAS WORTH IT.
- I DIDN'T KNOW A MUFFIN TASTES
SO MUCH BETTER WARM.
- AND TOASTED.
MM, I ALWAYS DO THAT.
- YAY, I'M EXCITED.
CLEANING.
- WANT ME TO HELP YOU?
- NO, I'M GONNA CLEAN,
AND THEN I'M GONNA PEE,
AND I DON'T WANT YOU
TO HELP ME PEE.
- CAN I PAINT A PENIS
ON YOUR WALL?
- NO.
- ALL RIGHT, MOM.
- DO YOU WANT TO START LAUNDRY
OR ANYTHING?
- I ALREADY DID MY LAUNDRY.
- OH.
- I WONDER IF
OUR FIRE ALARM WORKS?
IT LOOKS OLD.
I THINK WE SHOULD TEST IT OUT.
- NO, I JUST WANT TO CLEAN.
- IT'S, LIKE, BROWN.
DOES THE FIREMEN AUTOMATICALLY
COME, OR YOU CALL THEM?
YOU CALL THEM, I FEEL.
DID YOU EVER PULL A FIRE ALARM
IN YOUR HIGH SCHOOL?
- NO.
- I DID, AND I NEVER GOT CAUGHT.
I'M PIGGING OUT.
- I DON'T WANT TO BE THE ONLY
ONE CLEANING THIS WHOLE PLACE.
- YOU'RE NOT. RELAX.
I THINK YOU SHOULD CALL ROGER.
SEE IF HE'S STILL BEING
A DOUCHE.
IT'S LIKE SOMETIMES HE'S MORE
OF A DAD, LIKE, YELLING AT YOU.
- [bleep].
I'M GONNA CALL ROGER BACK
RIGHT NOW,
BECAUSE I REALLY DON'T KNOW
WHERE OUR RELATIONSHIP STANDS,
AND ON TOP OF IT,
I REALLY DO NEED
TO KNOW ABOUT THIS WEEKEND.
[phone ringing]
- HELLO?
- I WAS JUST WONDERING
IF YOU WERE COMING TONIGHT, SO
I CAN CONFIRM THE RESERVATION.
- HONESTLY, EVERYTHING
YOU SAID TO ME
EARLIER WAS SO MUMBO JUMBO--
- DO YOU UNDERSTAND HOW
YOU SOUND, THOUGH?
- OKAY, I'M OUT OF LINE?
OKAY, ENJOY YOUR WEEKEND, JENNI.
HAVE A GOOD WEEKEND.
- BUT YOU KNOW THE ONE THING
THAT HURTS ME THE MOST,
THE [bleep] MOST, IS WHEN
YOU CANCEL ON ME THE DAY OF.
- LOOK WHAT YOU DO TO ME!
WHAT I DO TO YOU--
- I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING!
- WHAT I DO TO YOU, JENNI--
- I DIDN'T EVEN [bleep]--
DO ANYTHING, THAT'S THE--
- ISN'T AS [bleep] IN THE--
[bleep] COMPARED
TO WHAT YOU DO TO ME.
- THAT'S THE THING RIGHT HERE,
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING
DIRECTLY TO YOU.
I APOLOGIZED TO YOU.
- YOU HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING
TO ME, JENNI?
- I SAID I'M SORRY.
- WE HAVEN'T HAD--
WE HAVEN'T HAD A YEAR
AND A HALF OF DEBATES
OVER THIS EXACT SAME THING,
AND EVERY SINGLE TIME
YOU HAVE COMPLETELY LIED TO ME?
- I'VE NOT--I JUST SAID SORRY.
I'M JUST TRYING
TO FIGURE IT OUT.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO,
RUIN THE WEEKEND?
GO BY MYSELF?
WHY DOES IT HAVE TO GO THAT FAR?
- BECAUSE YOU INSULT
MY INTELLIGENCE.
- I'M NOT, THOUGH.
THAT'S THE ISSUE.
I'M NOT DOING ANYTHING
BESIDES TRYING TO MAKE
[bleep] DINNER RESERVATIONS.
- YOU, HONESTLY, HAVE TO HURT
JENNI'S FEELINGS A LOT
TO HAVE HER CRY,
AND RIGHT NOW I WANT
TO SHOOT ROGER IN THE HEAD.
- HOW MANY HEATED,
CONTROVERSIAL ARGUMENTS--
- IT DOESN'T MATTER, THOUGH!
LISTEN HOW--
LISTEN TO WHAT
YOU'RE ACTUALLY MAD OVER.
- THAT I'M BEING LIED TO.
THAT'S WHAT I'M MAD OVER.
- [crying] MM, I CAN'T--
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
[sniffles]
- I'M GLAD I GOT OUR FAMILIES
AND FRIENDS
FOR THIS, UH,
SPECIAL MOMENT TOGETHER.
LET'S ENJOY IT.
- WHAT ABOUT ME?
- OH.
[laughter]
- KISS ME.
- OH.
[laughter]
- [crying] MM, I CAN'T--
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
- WELL, OKAY, JENNI, YOU WANT TO
PAINT ME OUT TO BE THE BAD GUY--
- I AM NOT PAINTING YOU OUT
TO BE LIKE ANYTHING.
I AM ACTUALLY TELLING
YOU YOU'RE RIGHT.
I APOLOGIZED.
I SAID I'M SORRY.
I TRIED TO MAKE IT
TO HAVE A GOOD WEEKEND.
- FAIR ENOUGH.
I WILL NEED ANSWERS EVENTUALLY,
BUT I'LL LET IT GO FOR NOW.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL SEE YOU
IN A LITTLE BIT.
- MM, BYE.
- BYE.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- NOTHING, HE'S JUST A [bleep].
AT THIS POINT, I DON'T KNOW
IF ME AND ROGER ARE GONNA LAST,
BUT HOW WE'RE COMMUNICATING
RIGHT NOW IS NOW ALL RIGHT,
AND I FEEL LIKE THIS COULD
ACTUALLY PUSH US OVER THE EDGE.
I'M TRYING TO COOL OFF BEFORE
I [bleep]
SAY [bleep] I DON'T MEAN.
[door locks]
- OY!
- * THERE'S NO ONE ELSE
I'D RATHER *
* SEE PUT UP AGAINST A WALL *
* YOU'VE GOT IT ALL WRONG-- *
- CAN YOU GET IT?
- IT'S PROBABLY JIONNI.
I SUPPOSE SO.
- YO.
- HI, ROG.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- I THOUGHT YOU WEREN'T
GONNA SHOW.
- WHY NOT?
- THE SCREAMING-FEST I HEARD.
- I'M TRYING NOT TO LET
MY EMOTIONS GET THE BEST
OF ME RIGHT NOW.
- HI.
- BUT I DON'T KNOW IF I'M GONNA
HOLD IT TOGETHER THIS WEEKEND.
LIKE, NOTHING
CAN BRIGHTEN MY DAY,
NOTHING CAN MAKE IT BETTER.
- QUIET IN HERE.
- YEAH.
[doorbell ringing]
- THERE'S YOUR BOO.
- HI.
- HEY, MUSCLE.
- WHAT'S UP, BUDDY?
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- JIONNI GETS HERE,
AND IT'S, LIKE,
REALLY SILENT IN THE ROOM,
AND AWKWARD.
- CAN I HAVE A FIBER BAR?
- HERE YOU GO.
- IT'S JENNI'S NUVARING.
- WHAT IS THAT?
- YOU SMELLED IT. [laughs]
- UGH, I SWEAR TO GOD.
DUDE, I'M LEAVING.
[all laughing]
- HE SNIFFED IT, JENNI.
- WHY DO YOU KEEP IT
IN THE REFRIGERATOR.
IT'S WEIRD.
- 'CAUSE THEY'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE REFRIGERATED.
- JIONNI IS SUCH A DORK,
BUT THE BOYS WERE LAUGHING,
JENNI WAS, LIKE, LAUGHING
WITH THEM, AND, YOU KNOW,
IT PUTS EVERYONE
IN A GOOD MOOD.
SO I THINK WE'RE ALL GONNA HAVE
A GOOD TIME TONIGHT.
- WE'RE GOING RIGHT NOW.
- IT'S A SURPRISE.
- COME ON, ROG.
- A SURPRISE TO JUST ME,
OR A SURPRISE TO ME AND JIONNI?
- THIS IS A FUN SURPRISE.
- COOL.
- WE'RE BRINGING THEM
TO LUCKY CHENG'S.
IT'S A DRAG SHOW DINNER PLACE.
THINK I PULLED MY ASS BONE.
- I'VE GOT YOU.
[all laughing]
- ALL RIGHT, IS THIS INDIAN?
[crowd chattering]
- NO, THIS IS--
IT'S NOT INDIAN.
- WHOSE NAME IS IT UNDER?
- IT'S UNDER MY NAME.
- THAT'S A GUY.
THAT WAS A GUY.
THAT WAS A GUY, ROG.
- I KNOW.
- IT'S ALL GUYS DRESSED
LIKE GIRLS.
- I KNOW.
OH, IT REALLY IS?
- YEAH.
- WAIT, I THOUGHT THIS WAS
A BIG JOKE.
THEY REALLY ARE GUYS?
I HAD NO IDEA.
- WE'RE ABOUT TO WATCH
A SHOW.
- NO WONDER ALL THE GIRLS
ARE LOOKING AT ME.
SO THIS SURPRISE
TURNS OUT TO BE
ALL GUYS DRESSED UP AS GIRLS.
- HI, GUYS, HOW ARE YA?
- GOOD.
- YOU ALL VIRGINS?
- NOT ME.
- ME EITHER, HONEY.
- YES.
- DO YOU LIKE CHOCOLATE?
- I LOVE CHOCOLATE.
- YOU LIKE CHOCOLATE WITH NUTS?
[all laughing]
- NICE! THAT WAS A GOOD ONE.
THAT WAS A GOOD ONE.
- I'M JUST TEASING, HONEY.
- JIONNI AND ROGER'S FACES
RIGHT NOW ARE PRICELESS.
I JUST FEEL LIKE THEY'RE
SO UNCOMFORTABLE THAT
IT'S CAUSING ME TO SMILE.
- STOP!
BOTH OF THEM, BOTH OF THEM,
BOTH OF THEM.
[crowd cheering]
- HANDS DOWN, LAST TIME JENNI
AND NICOLE ARE EVER
SURPRISING ME AND ROGER.
YOU KNOW I HATE YOU.
- [laughs]
- [bleep]
WELL, I'M GUESSING WE'LL GET
A LAP DANCE BY A GUY RIGHT NOW.
[both laughing, shouting]
- THAT'S WHAT HE GETS!
THAT'S WHAT HE GETS.
- WHOA.
[cheers and laughter]
[both laughing]
- I WANT TO RUN OFF STAGE
RIGHT NOW.
I SEE JENNI, NICOLE, THEY'RE
LAUGHING, HAVING A GOOD TIME,
WHILE I'M GETTING
BRACIOLA IN MY FACE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- [laughing]
I WAS LAUGHING SO HARD,
BECAUSE THEY'RE GETTING
MORE THAN JERSEY TURNPIKED
BY THESE QUEENS.
LIKE, IT'S PRETTY INTENSE.
- JIONNI, DO YOU LIKE
CHOCOLATE SURPRISE?
[cheers]
- IT GOT A LITTLE CRAZY.
I'M NOT GONNA LIE.
IT GOT A LITTLE CRAZY,
IT GOT--I WAS A LITTLE SCARED.
IT WAS DEFINITELY THE CRAZIEST
THING I'VE EVER DONE IN MY LIFE.
- I NEED A SHOT, RIGHT NOW.
I NEED SOMETHING TO DRINK,
RIGHT NOW.
- I NEED TO WASH MY HANDS.
- I'M GONNA KILL YOU.
- SHE MADE THE RESERVATION.
- *BABY, I'D RIDE FOR YOU,
DIE FOR YOU, LIE FOR YOU *
*AND IF I GOT LOCKED AWAY *
- WELL, WHAT TIME
IS DINNER AT JIONNI'S?
- WE USUALLY EAT AROUND,
LIKE, 4:00, 5:00.
I'M ABOUT TO GO TO
JIONNI'S HOUSE
TO HAVE, UM,
OUR FIRST ENGAGEMENT DINNER.
OBVIOUSLY OUR FIRST.
IT'S GONNA BE OUR FIRST
AND OUR LAST.
- ANYTHING WEIRD I SHOULD
BE KNOWING ABOUT GOING IN THERE?
- [chuckles] NO.
- WHAT'S JIONNI'S--
- JUST DON'T BE SCARED,
'CAUSE HIS MOM'S GONNA
PROBABLY THROW A LOT
OF FOOD AT YOU.
- WHAT'S HIS FAMILY LIKE?
- TYPICAL ITALIAN--
LOUD, FUN--
- LIKE--IT'S LIKE GOING TO,
LIKE, VINNIE'S HOUSE?
- YEAH, BUT NOT SO CRAZY.
I'M EXCITED.
- TONIGHT, ME AND ROGER
ARE GONNA GO TO
NICOLE'S ENGAGEMENT DINNER.
YOU KNOW, I WANT TO REALLY GET
TO KNOW HIS FAMILY AS WELL.
- SEE YOU SOON.
[screams]
[laughs]
[bleep] MY LIFE!
- DO YOU HAVE ALL
THE APPETIZERS SET, MA?
- YUP, YOU JUST HAVE TO TAKE OUT
THE CRAB CAKES AND THE--
- THE CRAB CAKES ARE DONE?
- CRAB CAKES ARE DONE, YEAH.
- HI!
- HI, HONEY.
- I MISSED YOU.
- I FEEL LIKE
WE'RE GONNA REMEMBER
THIS MOMENT FOR
THE REST OF OUR LIVES.
HI.
SO I'M REALLY EXCITED TO SEE
HOW OUR FAMILIES
CLASH TOGETHER.
- NO ONE'S HERE YET?
- MY MOM--MY MOM ASKED
IF YOU HAD A LITTLE BELLY.
- MM.
- HI, LITTLE BELLY.
HI, LITTLE BELLY.
- COOL.
IT'S ALL FAT RIGHT NOW.
- HOW YOU FEELING?
- GOOD.
I'M OVER, LIKE,
THE TIREDNESS NOW.
- OH, GOOD.
YOU LOOK GOOD.
- SO, I'M LIKE, I HAVE ENERGY.
[doorbell ringing]
- HELLO!
- HI!
- OH, MY GOD.
- OH, BOY.
- HI.
- WE GOT NICOLE'S
PARENTS COMING.
WE INVITED JENNI, ROGER--
- HI, HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD, HOW ARE YOU?
- AND MY UNCLE JOEY,
WITH HIS WIFE, CELESTE.
- WHAT'S THIS?
- CHAMPAGNE.
WE GOTTA CRACK IT.
- FIRST TIME EVERYONE'S
GONNA TALK ABOUT,
YOU KNOW, THIS UPCOMING YEAR.
- THEY'RE YOUR FAVORITES.
- I KNOW.
- IT'S ALL ABOUT NICOLE TODAY.
- YUP.
- EXCUSE ME.
- JUST TODAY, JOE?
[all laughing]
- YEAH, REALLY.
- I GUESS YOU'D KNOW TOO, HUH?
- I LIKE YOUR FUTURE FATHER-
AND MOTHER-IN-LAW, I REALLY DO.
- ME TOO.
- I'M GLAD I GOT OUR FAMILIES
AND FRIENDS
FOR THIS, UH,
SPECIAL MOMENT TOGETHER.
LET'S ENJOY IT.
- WHAT ABOUT ME?
- OH.
[all laughing]
GOOD HEALTH, TO MY LITTLE BABY--
- KOOTCHIE, KOOTCHIE.
- AND TO MY FIANCEE.
- KISS ME.
- OH.
[all laughing]
- IN THE CAR.
- OKAY, GO ON, GO INSIDE.
COME SIT DOWN, SIT DOWN.
CAN WE FIT THIS RIGHT
IN FRONT OF ROGER?
- PUT THIS HERE.
- WE HAVE CHICKEN PARM,
AND THAT'S IT.
- JIONNI, WE'RE WAIT--
WHERE'S GRACE?
WE'RE WAITING FOR GRACE.
- WHO'S GRACE?
[all chuckling]
- THANK YOU FOR
ALL THESE BLESSINGS,
AND THESE WONDERFUL PEOPLE
AT THIS TABLE.
all: AMEN.
- SALUTE.
- DELICIOUS, JANICE.
- THANK YOU.
- EVERYTHING YOU CREATED
AT THIS TABLE IS WONDERFUL.
EXCEPT FOR YOUR SON.
[all chuckling]
- OH, COME ON.
- ROGER'S MY GOOD FRIEND.
ROGER MAKES ME FUN
OF ME A LOT.
ROGER CALLS ME UP, HE GOES,
"HEY," HE GOES,
"I GOTTA--I GOTTA DROP
JENNI OFF," HE GOES,
"CAN YOU DRIVE ME BACK
TO TOMS RIVER."
I SAID, "YEAH, NO PROBLEM."
I SAID, "ALL RIGHT, YOU KNOW,
I'LL DRIVE YOU BACK."
HE DIDN'T SAY ONE NICE THING
[all laughing]
ABOUT ME THE WHOLE HOUR
AND A HALF.
OH, IT WAS A BAD RIDE.
YOU WANT ANOTHER ONE?
[indistinct chattering]
- THIS LASAGNA BOLOGNESE
WITH THE MEAN IN THERE, YEAH.
- IF YOU LIKE TO EAT,
THIS IS THE PLACE TO BE.
- I DO LIKE TO EAT.
- OH! IS THAT YOU?
- JIONNI, YOU REALLY WANT
TO DO THAT?
- DON'T GIVE ROG THE BABY ONE.
- [laughs]
- 'CAUSE YOU'RE, LIKE, ON A--
OH, MY GOD, HOW CUTE ARE YOU?
A BOOGIE BOARD.
I HOPE SHE'S NOT HATING.
- YOUR HEAD'S LIKE 42 POUNDS,
AND THE REST OF YOUR
BODY WEIGHS 12 POUNDS.
- OH, MY GOD!
- DO YOU KNOW WHICH ONE'S ME?
- RIGHT HERE.
[all laughing]
OH, MY GOD, YOU'RE LIKE
A LITTLE TINY THING IN THERE.
- WOW, LOOK AT YOUR JUMPSUIT.
- HE'S STANDING WHILE
THE PEOPLE ARE SITTING.
- I'M TALL FOR AN ITALIAN, ROG.
- JIONNI'S BABY PICTURES
WERE ADORABLE.
- I WAS A CUTE BABY,
SO WE HAVE TO HAVE
A [bleep] GORGEOUS KID.
[all laughing]
- ALL RIGHT--
- IT WON'T GO OVER.
- PICTURES AWAY.
THAT'S IT. THAT'S ENOUGH.
THE BABY PICTURES--
LOADED ROG WITH AMMUNITION
FOR AT LEAST THE NEXT TEN YEARS,
JUST HAMMERING ME.
- JANICE, IT WAS DELICIOUS.
- THANK YOU.
- EXCELLENT.
- ROGER!
- WHAT?
- COME DOWN.
COME DOWN HERE.
HANG OUT.
- I WASH THE DISHES
ALL THE TIME AT OUR HOUSE.
- YOU DO?
- YEAH, I LIKE WASHING.
- OKAY.
- NICOLE WANTS
TO WASH ALL THE DISHES.
- TO THE BEST LIFE, COMING UP.
- ABSOLUTELY.
SO WHAT'S UP, BUDDY?
ARE YOU REALLY READY FOR
THIS [bleep] MOVE, OR WHAT?
- WHAT MOVE?
- TO FATHERHOOD.
[chuckles]
LIKE YOU--I MEAN,
THAT'S A HUGE THING, BRO.
- OF COURSE I'M READY.
- OBVIOUSLY, I LIKE JIONNI.
HE'S MY FRIEND.
BUT HE'S GOT A CHILD
ON THE WAY,
SO IT'S GONNA BE
A REAL REALITY CHECK.
I DON'T KNOW IF HE HAS
EVERYTHING KIND OF LAID OUT
AND PLANNED OUT THE WAY
HE SHOULD YET.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS GONNA DO?
I MEAN, ARE YOU GONNA STAY
HERE AND LIKE--
- UM--
- WHEN SHE HAS THE BABY,
ARE YOU GONNA STAY HERE?
- FOR STARTERS,
I THINK WE'RE GONNA STAY--
BUT IT'S A COMFORT THING,
YOU KNOW, WHY NOT?
- YEAH.
- YOU KNOW, IF MY MOM'S HERE--
- IF YOU HAVE THE BABY,
AND YOU STAY HERE, YOU DEVELOP
THAT COMFORTABILITY FACTOR
WHERE YOU HAVE MOM, YOU KNOW,
THE EASE OF MOM BEING HERE,
- THAT'S--THAT'S WHAT I MEAN.
- HELPING YOU RAISE IT.
THEN YOU'RE NOT GONNA WANT
TO GO, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- I KNOW--I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING.
- OKAY.
- AND THIS IS
THE RIGHT DECISION.
- I RESPECT YOUR--RESPECT YOUR
CHOICES AND YOUR DECISIONS.
I'M NOT YOUR DAD.
I'M NOT TRYING TO BE.
HAVING A BABY IS GOING
TO BE THE MOST
LIFE-ALTERING EXPERIENCE
YOU'VE EVER HAD.
- NO [bleep], YOU KNOW?
THAT'S WHY I'VE
GOT GREAT EXPERIENCE.
THREE OF MY SIBLINGS
HAVE BABIES.
- I DON'T THINK THAT MEANS
THAT YOU KNOW
EVERYTHING THERE IS TO KNOW
ABOUT CHILD REARING.
- TRUST ME, I DO.
- THAT'S A NAIVE STATEMENT,
MY FRIEND.
- YUP.
- IT'S AN EXTREMELY
NAIVE STATEMENT.
- IT'S--SOMETIMES IT'S GOOD
TO HEAR SOMEONE ELSE'S,
YOU KNOW, POINT OF VIEW.
BUT, ROG,
YOU'VE GOT TO WORRY ABOUT YOUR
RELATIONSHIP, YOU KNOW?
IT'S NOT LIKE YOURS
IS PEACHES AND CREAM.
RIGHT NOW, YOU KNOW,
I'M DOING VERY WELL.
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH YOURS?
WE'RE ALL SET.
WHAT MORE DO WE NEED?
- [laughs] A LOT.
- THERE'S MORE SNOOKI AND JWOWW
ON THE WAY,
AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
- YOU'RE AMAZING.
- SEE YOU AGAIN SOON.
- I'LL SEE YOU IN
A LITTLE BIT, BUDDY.
- MOM, I REALLY CAN'T WAIT
TO COME ON A SUNDAY.
- YOU'RE NOT
OUT OF TROUBLE YET.
- ROG, THANK YOU, HONEY.
- THANK YOU...SO MUCH.
- AS SOON AS
THE POOL'S OPEN.
- SEE YOU SOON.
- THANK YOU AGAIN.
- THANK YOU.
- BYE, ROG.
THE NIGHT'S OVER,
WE SAY OUR GOOD-BYES,
GIVE MY PARENTS
THE HUG AND KISS.
"THANK YOU FOR TONIGHT."
NICOLE AND I ARE OUT.
- NIKKI, DRIVE SAFE, HON.
- WHOO!
- I THINK I OD-ed.
- CLOSE OUR DOOR!
- OH.
"CLOSE OUR DOOR."
- [grunts]
MY GOD, I'M SO FULL.
- JENNI.
- I JUST NEED A NAP.
- THAT'S A HOT MESS RIGHT THERE,
JUST GOING IMMEDIATELY TO BED.
- SO, I ATE MYSELF
INTO A FOOD COMA.
I'M TIRED, AND INCAPABLE
OF DOING ANYTHING.
- [growls]
- COMING.
- [sighs]
- BABY--MM--STOP.
- [whispering]
- [half asleep, mumbles]
BABE, PLEASE DON'T, I JUST--
PLEASE?
- [grunts]
I WAKE UP THIS MORNING,
AND I DIDN'T GET LAID.
SO NO SURPRISE THERE.
- AW, THAT MIGHT
BE THE CUTEST THING
I'VE EVER SEEN RIGHT THERE.
- SHH, THAT WAS CUTE, BUDDY.
- WANT ME TO CARRY YOU
TO THE BATHROOM?
[dog barking]
- HUH?
- LOOKED LIKE A LITTLE--
- I'D LIKE YOU TO SEE--
CARRY HER, I LIKE--
- LOOKED LIKE A LITTLE
KOALA BEAR CARRYING AN ACORN.
DID YOU HAVE SEX LAST NIGHT?
[dog barking]
- THAT'S NONE OF YOUR
[bleep] DAMN BUSINESS.
- I'M ASKING YOU
A [bleep] QUESTION.
YOU WILL ANSWER IT, SIR.
- NO.
- NO, YOU DIDN'T?
- CUDDLED WITH MY FIANCEE, MAN.
- WE DEFINITELY DID NOT.
I CAN ASSURE YOU, IT WAS NOT
FROM LACK OF EFFORT ON MY PART.
- I ALREADY KNEW YOU DIDN'T
DO IT, BECAUSE
THE PLACE WASN'T SHAKING.
- WE HAVE TO STOP AT THE PAWN
STORE ON THE WAY HOME.
TO SEE--
- FOR WHAT?
- TO SEE WHAT I CAN GET
FOR JENNI'S VAGINA,
'CAUSE SHE DOESN'T
USE IT ANYMORE.
- [laughs]
THAT WAS A GOOD ONE.
HOW DO YOU LIVE WITH THIS GUY?
- I CAN'T.
- IT'S BEEN TWO DAYS,
AND I REALLY WANNA--
- [laughs]
- ONE EXTREME OR THE OTHER.
- I LIKE GRUMPY ROGER BETTER.
- YEAH, ME TOO.
THE WEEKEND ACTUALLY
WENT PRETTY WELL,
FROM THE EXPECTATIONS I HAD
A COUPLE DAYS AGO,
WITH THE HUGE FIGHT
WITH ME AND ROGER.
- BYE.
- YOU LOOK LIKE A PENGUIN.
I'LL TAKE GOOD CARE
OF YOUR BOYFRIEND.
- WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
- AW, SEE, THAT'S TRUE LOVE.
- YOU SHOULD GIVE ROGER A HUG.
- I FEEL LIKE WE'RE ABLE
TO END ON A GOOD NOTE,
AND I'M HAPPY WITH THAT.
YOU DIDN'T EVEN SAY GOOD-BYE
TO YOUR--MWAH--CHILDREN.
- YOU'RE A NICE LADY.
- WHY DO YOU NEVER SAY GOOD-BYE
TO YOUR CHILDREN?
- 'CAUSE THEY'RE
MY ADOPTED CHILDREN.
I DON'T REALLY CARE ABOUT THEM.
NOBODY DOES.
- I LOVE YOU.
I'M GONNA GO GIVE THEM BACON,
SINCE THEIR FATHER
DOESN'T LOVE THEM.
- PUB!
- WHAT?
- WHEN DO YOU WANT TO GO TO EAT?
- WHEN WOULD YOU LIKE TO LEAVE?
- A.S.A.P.!
- ARE YOU DRESSED?
- I'M NOT GETTING DRESSED UP.
IT'S A DINER.
- I THINK I'LL DRIVE.
- LET'S GO.
[dog barking]
ME AND JENNI
LOVE BROWNSTONE DINER,
AND WE JUST NEED SOME PANCAKES
IN OUR LIVES.
- I'M EXHAUSTED FROM THIS WEEK.
- I'VE BEEN EXHAUSTED SINCE
WE MOVED IN.
I THINK IT'S MORE LIKE THIS--
DONE!
- YEAH.
WE NEED A VACATION.
- CANCUN!
DO THEY HAVE CREATURES
IN CANCUN?
- LIKE A--
- LIKE A SAFARI.
THAT WOULD BE COOL.
- WE RIDE ON ONE OF THOSE, LIKE,
- SO, LIKE GO AND--
YEAH, THEN WE SEE ANIMALS.
- RANGER THINGS?
- YEAH.
SO, I THINK IT WOULD
BE A GREAT IDEA
IF ME AND JENNIE GO TO CANCUN.
BECAUSE IT IS SPRING BREAK,
AND I'M SURE
THERE'S A LOT OF THINGS GOING
ON IN CANCUN.
AND WE CAN SEE ANIMALS,
AND JUST HAVE, LIKE,
A RELAXING WEEKEND.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- SINCE WE'RE WITH
THE BOYS ALL THE TIME,
MAYBE IT SHOULD
BE ALL GIRLFRIENDS.
SO IT COULD BE LIKE
A GIRLS' WEEKEND.
- I LIKE THAT IDEA.
I FEEL LIKE
I SHOULD TAKE YANICE.
- I WANT TO TAKE RYDER.
I HAVEN'T REALLY HUNG
OUT WITH HER
SINCE I TOLD HER
I WAS PREGNANT AND ENGAGED.
- REALLY?
- YEAH.
- I REALLY HOPE THEY CAN GO.
- CANCUN!
I CAN'T WAIT.
- OH, MY GOD.
- WE'RE IN CANCUN!
[all screaming, cheering]
- IT'S GONNA BE A GOOD
[bleep] TIME IN CANCUN.
- THERE'S A FIGHT BREAKING OUT.
YOU KNOW, GOD FORBID I GOT HURT
AND LOST THE BABY, LIKE,
I'M HONESTLY SCARED.
- NICOLE!
- STOP SCREAMING AT ME.
- NICOLE IN CANCUN SUCKS.
YOU KNOW,
I WISH SHE DIDN'T COME.
- I FEEL BAD.
- [crying] I DON'T THINK I WANT
TO LIVE WITH JENNI ANYMORE.