- I HOPE HE
COMES TONIGHT.
- HE FLAKES OUT ON ME
ALL THE TIME.
I NEED TO GET OUT
OF THIS HOUSE.
WE'RE IN CANCUN!
- IT'S [bleep]ING 2:00
IN THE MORNING.
I SHOULDN'T BE HERE.
- NICOLE!
- STOP SCREAMING AT ME.
- JUST BE CONSIDERATE.
- YOU BE CONSIDERATE.
I'M PREGNANT
AND WE'RE ALL, "WHOO!"
- I FEEL BAD.
[line ringing]
- [crying] I DON'T THINK
I WANT TO LIVE
WITH JENNI ANYMORE.
[Icona Pop's I Love It]
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT,
* I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE *
* *
- [crying] I DON'T EVEN KNOW
IF I WANNA LIVE
WITH JENNI ANYMORE.
- WHAT?
- I DON'T THINK
I WANNA LIVE
WITH JENNI ANYMORE.
- WHY?
WHY, WHAT'S THE MATTER
- SHE JUST DOESN'T
GET IT AT ALL.
- I FEEL BAD.
- IT'S HER CHOICE.
- AND THEN TONIGHT
SHE TOLD ME
TO BE CONSIDERATE
AND I'M, LIKE,
"ARE YOU SERIOUS?"
AND, LIKE, I'M PREGNANT.
LIKE, A FIGHT BROKE OUT.
JUST--IT'S NOT
MY SCENE ANYMORE.
I GUESS I'M JUST
NOT HAVING FUN IN CANCUN.
I JUST FEEL ALONE
AND PREGNANT
AND MY TWO BEST FRIENDS
AREN'T THERE TO SUPPORT ME.
- YOU KNOW,
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT ELSE TO TELL YOU
AT THIS POINT, HONEY.
YOU KNOW, RIDE IT OUT
AND JUST
MAKE THE BEST OF IT
UNTIL YOU--
- I'VE BEEN THIS WHOLE
[bleep]ING TIME.
- SHE WAS, LIKE,
CRYING ABOUT
HOW IT'S SPRING BREAK
AND SHE'S HERE
AND SHE CAN'T DO ANYTHING.
- SHE DOESN'T WANT
TO DO ANYTHING.
I'VE SEEN WOMEN
THAT WORK 18-HOUR DAYS,
SEVEN MONTHS PREGNANT.
NICOLE IS DELIBERATELY
MAKING HERSELF MISERABLE.
SHE'S NOT THE CENTER
OF ATTENTION,
AND THEREFORE
SHE'LL RUIN EVERYONE'S TIME.
- I UNDERSTAND,
BECAUSE YOU CAN'T DRINK
AND YOU CAN'T PARTY
LIKE YOU'RE USED TO DOING
AND EVERYTHING ELSE,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN YOU CAN'T
MAKE THE BEST OF IT, NICOLE.
- YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND
AT ALL.
I'M ENGAGED AND PREGNANT
AND I JUST--
MY PRIORITIES I THINK
ARE A LITTLE MESSED UP
RIGHT NOW.
MY WHOLE LIFE
IS DIFFERENT FROM
THESE THREE GIRLS,
AND ALL THEY WANT TO DO
IS HAVE FUN AND ENJOY
THEMSELVES AND, YOU KNOW,
IT SUCKS FOR ME,
AND I'M KIND OF ASKING MYSELF
"WHAT THE [bleep]
AM I DOING HERE?"
- BELIEVE ME, IT'S JUST A
PART OF LIFE, HON, BELIEVE ME--
- HAVE FUN.
HOLD ON, DAD.
BYE.
- BYE.
- HAVE FUN.
- YEAH, BYE.
- LOVE YOU.
- WHO PUTS A CARPET
IN A HOTEL ROOM?
- WHOA!
- IT KIND OF SUCKS,
LIKE, I DEFINITELY FEEL
LEFT OUT RIGHT NOW.
AND I'M NEVER LEFT OUT
SO IT'S JUST--
IT'S VERY HARD
WHEN I AM LEFT OUT,
BECAUSE I'M NOT USED TO IT.
I'M SAD.
- ALL RIGHT,
IT'S JUST--HONEY,
IT'S JUST A PART
OF LIFE, HON.
AND WE'VE ALL BEEN THERE.
- [laughs]
all: * WAAH-WAAH *
- IT'S NOT FAIR
THAT NICOLE'S SO MISERABLE,
BUT I'M NOT
LETTING IT STOP ME.
I'M GONNA
HAVE A GOOD TIME,
AND I'LL DEAL WITH THAT
[bleep] WHEN I GET HOME.
[upbeat electronic music]
* *
OH, MY GOD,
THIS PLACE IS KINDA COOL.
HOLY [bleep].
- GET THE [bleep] OUTTA HERE.
- OH, MY GOD.
- THE CITY IS INSANITY.
IT LOOKS LIKE AN ARENA.
* *
IT'S JUST BALLS-TO-THE-WALL
PARTYING, HAVE A GOOD TIME--
AND NICOLE IS BACK
AT THE HOTEL ROOM.
- I'M TRYING TO BE HEALTHY
AND I'M TRYING TO BE
A GOOD MOTHER.
BEING THE LAST NIGHT THERE,
SITTING ALONE
IN A HOTEL ROOM SUCKS.
ALL RIGHT,
I'M GONNA GO TO BED.
I LOVE YOU, BYE.
- BYE.
[Kari Kimmel's
One Day You'll Be Fine]
- * YOU TOLD ME TO FIGHT *
* I GAVE IT A TRY *
[steam whistle blows]
- WHOO!
- * AND HOPED THAT *
* YOU WERE RIGHT *
* I DON'T WANT TO STAY *
* TO MAKE IT OKAY *
* FOR JUST A WHILE *
- I DON'T CARE
IF YOU CALL ME
OVERDRAMATIC, INSECURE--
WHATEVER YOU WANNA CALL ME.
THAT REALLY [bleep]ING HURT.
GOOD-BYE.
ROGER FINALLY
HAS GONE WAY TOO FAR.
TO BE HONEST, I DON'T EVEN KNOW
IF WE'RE TOGETHER AT THIS POINT.
[line ringing]
- HELLO?
- HI.
I THINK I'LL BE HOME AROUND
7:30, 8:00 IF YOU WANNA
GET THERE A LITTLE AFTER 8:30.
- I DON'T KNOW
IF WE'RE COMING, BABE.
I JUST TALKED
TO JIONNI LAST NIGHT.
AND, UH, WE MADE PLANS
BASED UPON WHAT YOU TOLD ME.
- SO YOU'RE NOT COMING?
- NO, I MADE PLANS.
- YOU'RE SERIOUS RIGHT NOW?
- ARE YOU GONNA REALLY TRY
TO PUSH THIS AROUND ON ME?
- IN MY EYES, ROGER
IS BLOWING ME OFF RIGHT NOW
AFTER WE MADE PLANS,
AND I FEEL LIKE
THAT'S NOT WHAT
GOOD BOYFRIENDS DO.
I [bleep]ING MISS YOU.
- YOU TOLD ME
YOU WEREN'T GONNA BE HOME
UNTIL SUNDAY,
SO I MADE PLANS.
- YOU WANNA PICK
YOUR FRIENDS OVER ME,
SO [bleep]ING BE IT.
- DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA HOW
INSECURE YOU SOUND RIGHT NOW?
- WHAT DOES THAT EVEN HAVE--
[bleep]ING INSECURITY?
I [bleep]ING HAVEN'T
SEEN YOU IN A WEEK.
- I MEAN, THIS IS PROBABLY
THE WORST WAY TO BE WOKEN UP,
WITH JENNI AND ROGER SCREAMING.
THIS WHOLE VACATION
IS LIKE A ROLLER-COASTER,
AND I WANNA
[bleep]ING GET OFF.
- THIS IS WHAT I GET.
I GET THAT YOU'RE
GONNA GO OUT--
YOU CHOOSE NOT TO--
- OH, MY GOD.
COULD YOU PLAY
THE VICTIM ANY MORE?
- IT'S NOT THE VICTIM, YOU'RE
A PIECE OF [bleep] BOYFRIEND!
THAT'S WHAT THE [bleep]
YOU ARE RIGHT NOW.
- WHY DOESN'T NICOLE HAVE A
PROBLEM WITH JIONNI GOING OUT?
- I DON'T [bleep]ING
GIVE A [bleep]
ABOUT JIONNI
AND NICOLE'S RELATIONSHIP!
THEY ARE NOT MINE!
I DO NOT [bleep]ING
LIKE YOU RIGHT NOW!
PROVE YOUR [bleep]ING POINT
AND GO OUT WITH YOUR BOYS!
AND SEE HOW FAR
THAT GETS YOU WITH ME!
[phone beeps off]
- THANK YOU.
I AM SO BEYOND READY TO GET
THE [bleep] OUT OF MEXICO.
AND USUALLY YOU'RE EXCITED
TO GO ON VACATION.
I'M EXCITED TO GO BACK HOME
TO JERSEY CITY.
HOME SWEET HOME.
I FELT LEFT OUT
THE WHOLE TRIP.
ALL YOU GUYS WERE DOING
WAS TAKING SHOTS--"WHOO!"
I'M SITTING THERE SO AWKWARD.
BECAUSE YOU KNOW
I LOVE DRINKING--THAT'S, LIKE,
TORTURE TO BE FLAUNTING
IN MY FACE.
- I THOUGHT YOU LOVED
BEING PREGNANT THOUGH.
- I DO.
BUT I DON'T WANT
TO BE AROUND
THAT SCENARIO AT ALL
DURING MY PREGNANCY.
- I'VE HAD PREGNANT FRIENDS,
NINE MONTHS PREGNANT
AND ABLE TO HAVE FUN.
AND WE WERE, LIKE, "COOL,
SHE CAN'T HAVE FUN WITH US."
- I WOULD PROBABLY NEVER GO
ON VACATION AGAIN PREGNANT.
IT'S JUST NOT FUN.
- TAKE A NICE VACAY WITH JIONNI.
- I WONDER WHERE
THEY'RE GOING, ANYWAY?
I'M, LIKE, TRYING
TO THINK WHAT HE'S WEARING.
- OH, I JUST [bleep]ING
FORGOT ABOUT THAT.
- OH, SORRY.
- HE KEPT HIS PLANS WITH JIONNI
AND THEN CANCELLED FOR ME.
OH, I HATE GETTING BLOWN OFF.
[dial tone]
[phone buttons beeping]
[line ringing]
- [clears throat]
- HI, THIS IS JIONNI.
- AND ROGER.
- WE CAN'T GET TO THE PHONE
RIGHT NOW, PLEASE LEAVE
A MESSAGE AFTER THE BEEP.
- AND AN APOLOGY WOULD BE NICE
IF YOU EXPECT TO SEE ME
IN JERSEY CITY
ANYTIME SOON.
- LATER, BITCHES.
- [automated voice]
AT THE TONE,
PLEASE RECORD YOUR MESSAGE.
[voice mail beeps]
- YOU GUYS ARE SO ANNOYING.
- WHY WOULD I WANT TO APOLOGIZE
AFTER THEY SOUNDED LIKE
[bleep] JOEY?
- I DON'T EVEN WANT
TO TALK TO THEM.
- [laughs]
- [groans] "LATER, BITCHES."
- [laughs] OH,
THAT'S NOT EVEN RIGHT.
- IDIOTS.
- [automated voice] TO CONTINUE
RECORDING WHERE YOU LEFT OFF,
PRESS FOUR.
IF YOU'RE SATISFIED
WITH THE MESSAGE, PRESS ONE.
- [laughs] OH, MY GOD!
- [automated voice] TO LISTEN
TO YOUR MESSAGE, PRESS ONE.
- OH, IT'S STILL ON?
[laughter]
[screams] DID I SAY SOMETHING?
[dial tone]
DID I SAY SOMETHING BAD?
I DIDN'T ACTUALLY HANG UP,
AND EVERYTHING
THAT ME AND JENNI SAID
WAS RECORDED ON THE VOICEMAIL.
- WHAT'S UP?
- DON'T LISTEN
TO THAT LAST VOICEMAIL.
- WHY?
- 'CAUSE WE WERE TALKING
[bleep] AND I THOUGHT I HUNG UP.
- [laughs]
- MISS YOU.
- WHERE ARE YOU GUYS?
- UM, WE'RE AT CARMINE'S
RIGHT NOW.
- OH.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING AFTER?
- ACROSS THE STREET?
I DON'T KNOW,
HEMINGWAY'S MAYBE.
- THEY'RE GOING
TO HEMINGWAY'S!
- I THINK I'M ACTUALLY
GOING TO BREAK UP WITH HIM.
- [gasps]
- WHY ARE YOU
FREAKING OUT?
- THERE'S GONNA BE,
LIKE, GIRLS THERE.
- THERE'S NOT
GONNA BE GIRLS.
WE'RE NOT--NICOLE.
IF I WAS TRYING
TO HIDE [bleep] FROM YOU,
WE WOULDN'T LEAVE YOU GUYS
A MESSAGE JOKING AROUND.
- ALL RIGHT,
I'LL LET YOU GO.
YOU GUYS HAVE FUN.
HE'S ANNOYING.
- NOW I'M [bleep]ING PISSED.
- I'D RATHER JIONNI GO
ANYWHERE ELSE BUT HEMINGWAY'S.
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE
IT'S GONNA BE A PROBLEM.
- THAT'S HOW I FEEL.
- WHO ARE YOU CALLING?
- I'M CALLING HIM
NOT TO APOLOGIZE.
- OH, GOD, DO I NEED
TO GET EAR-MUFFS?
[dial tone]
[phone buttons beeping]
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
- I DON'T KNOW YET.
[dial tone]
- HELLO?
- YO.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN, "YO"?
- JUST YO.
- THAT'S HOW
YOU ANSWER THE PHONE?
- I SAID, "HELLO?"
- OH.
I'M NOT CALLING
TO APOLOGIZE,
BUT I GUESS
I'M GONNA EXPLAIN
MYSELF AS A HUMAN BEING,
BECAUSE OBVIOUSLY
I LEFT OFF SCREAMING.
I WAS COMING HOME EARLY.
I GOT REALLY EXCITED
THAT I COULD BE HOME WITH YOU,
BUT YOU GAVE ME ATTITUDE.
- NO, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I SPOKE WITH JIONNI...
- AND I AM TRYING--
- AND FOUND OUT
HE WASN'T GOING.
- BUT YOU HAVE
TO UNDERSTAND SOMETHING.
OUR RELATIONSHIP
IS NOT THEIR RELATIONSHIP
AND YOU KNOW WHAT--
- THAT'S FOR SURE.
- WHAT?
- THEY HAVE A BETTER ONE
THAN WE DO.
- ARE YOU REALLY GONNA
BE LIKE THIS RIGHT NOW?
- I'M GONNA SPEAK MY MIND
LIKE I ALWAYS DO.
I SURE AM.
- YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU DID?
YOU PUT ME IN
THE SAME MINDSET
THAT I WAS TWO YEARS AGO,
SOME INSECURE LITTLE [bleep]
THAT YOU DIDN'T
GIVE A [bleep] ABOUT.
- WHICH YOU ARE,
WHICH YOU ARE.
- I AM HURT.
I AM HURT.
AND IF YOU DON'T WANT
TO SPEAK TO ME
FOR THE REST OF THIS TIME,
I DON'T CARE.
BUT I AM GOING TO EXPLAIN
TO YOU--
- OKAY, NO PROBLEM,
I WON'T CALL YOU.
I ASSURE YOU OF THAT.
I WILL NOT CALL YOU.
- THIS IS--I'M TRYING TO BE
THE ADULT HERE FOR ONCE.
- OKAY, WELL, THAT'S FINE.
I UNDERSTAND THAT YOU'RE HURT,
AND I AM NOT
APOLOGIZING FOR ANYTHING.
I DID NOTHING WRONG.
YOU SHOULD BE WITH TOM.
YOU GUYS WERE PERFECT
FOR EACH OTHER.
- BY TELLING ME THAT
I SHOULD BE WITH MY EX,
HE CAN GO [bleep] HIMSELF,
AND HE CAN BURN IN HELL.
- NO, YOU CALLED ME THE MOST
INSECURE PERSON IN THE WORLD.
- YOU ARE, HANDS DOWN.
- EW, PLEASE DON'T CRY.
- HANDS DOWN.
- [crying] YOU TOLD ME
I DESERVE TO BE WITH MY EX.
- AT LEAST YOU AND TOM
TREATED EACH OTHER EQUAL.
AT LEAST.
- LISTEN TO YOU.
- YOU DO NOT TREAT ME EQUAL.
- NO! IT WASN'T EQUAL.
AND YOU DON'T KNOW
MY RELATIONSHIP WITH HIM.
AND HOW DARE YOU TELL ME
THAT I DESERVE--
THAT'S ALL I CAN GET.
- WELL, IT'S TRUTH
AND YOU HATE TRUTH.
- NO, I JUST DON'T LIKE YOU
BECAUSE I ACTUALLY
GENUINELY MISSED YOU.
AND I DON'T MISS YOU ANYMORE
AND THAT'S A PROBLEM.
[sniffling]
- YOU TOLD ME I DESERVE
TO BE WITH MY EX.
I DON'T CARE IF YOU CALL ME
OVERDRAMATIC, INSECURE--
WHATEVER YOU WANNA CALL ME.
THAT REALLY [bleep]ING HURT.
MY ONLY INTENTIONS
WERE TO SEE
THE BOYFRIEND OF TWO YEARS
THAT I HAVE.
OR WHATEVER
I HAVE LEFT OF.
ALL RIGHT?
- OKAY.
- GOOD-BYE.
WHAT A DOUCHE-BAG,
I HATE HIM.
- WHY DOES HE PUT YOU DOWN
LIKE THAT?
- I DON'T KNOW, IT HURTS.
- OH.
- [sniffling]
I [bleep]ING HATE MY EX,
AND THAT'S WHAT HE SAYS?
- I THINK HE KNOWS
THAT WASN'T
THE RIGHT THING
TO SAY.
- HE SAYS THE ONLY THINGS
THAT WILL [bleep]ING
HURT MY FEELINGS.
- SORRY.
- IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
- I FEEL BAD.
- I FEEL LIKE
HE JUST CROSSED
THE LINE THIS TIME.
- I THINK SO TOO.
I DON'T THINK HE REALIZES
HOW MEAN HE CAN BE.
- I'M NOT PERFECT,
I'LL ADMIT IT.
BUT I DON'T--
- NO ONE'S PERFECT.
I'M NOT [bleep]ING PERFECT.
- I DON'T THINK
I DESERVE THAT.
- YOU DON'T.
NO ONE DESERVES THAT.
- NICOLE'S BEING THERE
FOR ME RIGHT NOW.
NO MATTER HOW UPSET
OR PISSED OFF
SHE WAS AT ME
IN CANCUN,
LIKE, SHE'S STILL THERE
FOR ME RIGHT NOW.
- I FEEL LIKE HE,
LIKE, DUG HIS HOLE.
[laughs]
- I PULLED MY HAIR OUT.
- YOU'RE, LIKE, POPPING BLOOD
VESSELS, LOSING EXTENSIONS.
OH, MY GOD.
PLEASE.
- WHAT THE [bleep]?
I DON'T THINK ME AND ROGER
ARE GONNA MAKE IT THROUGH THIS
BECAUSE OF WHAT
HE SAID TO ME.
- GOOD NIGHT.
- GOOD NIGHT, LOVE YOU.
TO BE HONEST,
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
IF WE'RE TOGETHER
AT THIS POINT.
[Amber Rubarth's
One Last Look]
- * I FALL APART EVERY TIME *
* THAT I TAKE *
* ONE LAST LOOK AT YOU *
* *
- MORNING.
- HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
- LIKE [bleep].
WORST SLEEP EVER.
- 'CAUSE OF ROGER?
- MM-HM.
I'VE NEVER CRIED
SO HARD IN MY LIFE.
[bleep] EMBARRASSING.
I DIDN'T EVEN WANNA
GET OUT OF BED TODAY.
- I WOULD HAVE LAID
WITH YOU ALL DAY.
- YEAH, I WOULD HAVE.
- AND I REALLY DIDN'T
GET GOOD SLEEP LAST NIGHT,
AND I'M SURE YOU DIDN'T.
- DON'T YOU HEAR
MY STOMACH RIGHT NOW?
- MY STOMACH IS GROWING.
- IT'S A GOOD THING.
- LIKE, COME HERE,
FEEL RIGHT NOW.
LIKE, GO FROM--
NOT MY VAGINA-BONE,
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THAT'S CALLED.
- BUT RIGHT--JUST GO UP.
FEEL IT?
IT'S, LIKE, HARD.
LIKE, A PREGNANT STOMACH.
- EXCITED?
SO IT'S NOT
A WEIRD STOMACH ANYMORE?
IT'S A PREGNANT ONE?
- IT'S STARTING TO FORM.
I WAS SLEEPING LIKE THIS.
- [laughs]
- I WAS, LIKE, "GOOD NIGHT."
AS OF RIGHT NOW
IT'S STARTING TO FORM.
SO WHEN EVERYONE,
YOU KNOW,
STARTS TO TOUCH IT,
I FEEL LIKE I'M FINE RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE YOU CAN
ACTUALLY FEEL IT.
BUT YOU COULDN'T
FEEL IT BEFORE AND I'M, LIKE,
"[bleep]
STOP TOUCHING MY FAT."
both: [chuckling]
- ARE YOU DOING THE LAPTOP?
- YEAH, I'M GOOGLING
WHAT 14 WEEKS IS.
- I'M WONDERING
WHAT IT'S DOING IN THERE.
- "THIS WEEK'S
BIG DEVELOPMENTS.
YOUR BABY CAN NOW SQUINT..."
- EW.
- "FROWN.
- "GRIMACE, PEE,
AND POSSIBLY SUCK HIS THUMB."
- WHAT THE [bleep]
IS GRIMACE?
EW!
- "AND YOUR BABY
SEES LIGHT."
- WHAT LIGHT?
MY VAGINA HOLE?
- IT MAY MOVE IF YOU SHINE
A FLASHLIGHT AT YOUR BELLY.
- I WANNA TELL MY BABY
IN MORSE CODE,
"I'M SORRY IF IT'S WEIRD
IN THERE,
"BUT I CAN'T WAIT
TO SEE YOU.
"AND I'M SORRY
IF YOU FEEL DADDY'S PENIS
EVERY TIME WE HAVE SEX."
THERE'S A [bleep]ING CREATURE
INSIDE OF ME, IT'S SO WEIRD.
WHAT TIME IS COOKING CLASS?
- YOU WANT TO GO
TO COOKING CLASS WITH ME?
- YEAH.
- OH, REALLY?
- JENNI ASKED ME TO GO
TO THE COOKING CLASS
WITH HER LAST-MINUTE.
CLEARLY, SHE'S UPSET
AND I JUST FEEL REALLY BAD.
SO I'M JUST TRYING TO BE THERE
FOR JENNI RIGHT NOW.
- ALL RIGHT, CAN YOU GET
IN COMFY CLOTHES WITH ME THOUGH?
[dog barking]
- UH-UH.
- YOU'RE GONNA MAKE PASTA
IN THAT?
- YEAH.
OH, THIS IS WHERE IT IS?
- YOU DROPPED ME OFF.
- HI.
- HEY, GUYS.
- HI, SORRY WE'RE LATE.
- PAUL.
- NICOLE.
- HI, PAUL.
HI, BABE.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- HI.
- I'M NICOLE. NICE TO MEET YOU.
- I LIKE YOUR HAIR.
- THIS IS DEFINITELY
COOKING 101 FOR ME.
- THIS IS NICOLE.
- I'M CELESTE.
- HI.
- HI, NICOLE,
PLEASURE MEETING YOU.
- YOU TOO.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW
HOW TO COOK ANYTHING.
AND, YOU KNOW, HAVING A BABY
AND BEING A WIFE,
I NEED TO LEARN
HOW TO [bleep]ING COOK.
- OKAY, YOU GUYS,
WE ARE MAKING
A CHEESE RICOTTA RAVIOLI,
AND THAT'S GOING TO BE PAIRED
WITH FRESH TOMATO SAUCE.
- I THOUGHT PASTA
COMES IN A BOX.
- SERIOUSLY.
- YOU SEE HOW THE DOUGH
IS COMING TOGETHER?
I'M NOT A PERFECT...
- [whispers] UNCIRCUMCISED.
- EW.
IT LOOKS EXACTLY LIKE
AN UNCIRCUMCISED PENIS.
AND IT REALLY IS GROSSING ME OUT
BECAUSE IT'S DISGUSTING.
- SHE SHOWED ME
AN UNCIRCUMCISED PENIS,
AND I'M SCORNED FOR--
NO OFFENSE IF YOU HAVE ONE--
AND I'M SCORNED FOR LIFE.
- THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
crack!
- MAY I HAVE THAT OIL?
PASTA MAKING IS ACTUALLY
PRETTY FUN RIGHT NOW.
- OH!
[laughter]
YEAH, I THOUGHT IT WOULD
BE VERY, VERY HARD AND ANNOYING.
- MMM.
- BUT IT'S ACTUALLY FUN
TO, LIKE, MAKE THE DOUGH
AND THEN ROLL IT OUT
AND THEN MAKE SLICES.
IT'S FUN TO MAKE RAVIOLIS.
- UNCIRCUMCISED.
splat!
- [gasps]
- [laughs]
- [gasps] JENNI!
IT'S IN MY [bleep]ING
EYELASH NOW.
- I JUST STRIKED YOU
WITH AN UNCIRCUMCISED...
- COME ON!
- IT'S NOTHING NEW,
IT'S NOTHING NEW.
NICOLE, ALL OF SUDDEN
HAS A PROBLEM
WITH A LITTLE PENIS
ON HER FACE.
I FEEL LIKE ME AND ROGER
WOULD END UP IN A FISTFIGHT
IF WE DID THIS TOGETHER.
- ME AND JIONNI,
THIS WOULD BE A JOKE.
- AT LEAST YOU'RE
SOMEWHAT AGREEING WITH ME.
- I'M ON YOUR SIDE.
- OKAY, YOU'RE GONNA
START MAKING YOUR FILLING.
- I'M ON YOUR SIDE
EVEN WHEN YOU'RE WRONG.
- THAT'S WHAT
BEST FRIENDS ARE FOR.
- MM-HM.
- NICOLE SAW HOW UPSET I WAS
AND SHE WAS CONSOLING ME,
AND THAT'S WHAT
GOOD FRIENDS DO.
- FINALLY!
LIKE, I WOULD DIE FOR YOU.
- YEAH, 100%.
I WOULD TAKE
A BULLET FOR YOU.
- BUT LET'S MAKE SURE
THAT DOESN'T HAPPEN.
- YEAH.
- CHEERS TO THE SIX OF US.
- CHEERS.
- ITALIAN NIGHT
IN JERSEY CITY.
- THERE'S MORE SNOOKI AND JWOWW
ON THE WAY
AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
[phone buttons beeping]
[line ringing]
SO THIS MORNING
I JUST WANT TO CALL JIONNI
AND FIND OUT WHAT HAPPENED
AT THE BAR,
BECAUSE JENNI'S REALLY UPSET,
AND OBVIOUSLY I WANNA KNOW
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED.
- HELLO?
- HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
- THANKS.
- WHAT DID YOU DO LAST NIGHT?
- WE WENT TO, UH, HEMINGWAY'S.
- DID ROGER GO TO HEMINGWAY'S?
- YEAH, WE WERE
TOGETHER ALL NIGHT.
- OH, 'CAUSE HE WAS
REALLY MEAN TO JENNI.
WAS THERE GIRLS THERE?
- NO.
- DID THEY GET--
DID THEY HIT ON YOU?
- NO, NOT ONE PERSON
EVEN, LIKE, CAME UP TO ME.
- WITH JIONNI GOING OUT
TO THE BAR, I MEAN,
OBVIOUSLY IT'S DOWN
THE SHORE AND, YOU KNOW,
OBVIOUSLY THERE'S GONNA
BE GIRLS AT THIS BAR.
- BYE.
- ALL RIGHT, BYE.
SO I KIND OF HAVE,
LIKE, THIS BAD FEELING
THAT JIONNI HUNG OUT
WITH RANDOM GIRLS LAST NIGHT.
I WANNA DO SOME STALKING.
I DON'T LIKE STALKING JIONNI,
BUT WE'RE ENGAGED NOW,
SO I'M ALLOWED
TO DO THAT.
- "ROGER AND SNOOKI'S BOYFRIEND
AT HEMINGWAY'S TONIGHT."
CLICK ON HER.
- YOU GOTTA BE [bleep]ING
KIDDING ME, BRO.
THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
WELL, YOUR MAN'S
IN THE [bleep]ING CLEAR.
[scoffs]
- THEY'RE ALL OVER HIM.
LOOK, THEY'RE,
LIKE, TOUCHING SKIN.
OH, MY GOD,
I'M GONNA KILL SOMEONE
IF HE'S [bleep]ING
THESE SKANKS.
JIONNI IS IN THE PICTURE
WITH THESE GIRLS
AND HE'S TOUCHING SKINS
WITH ONE OF THE GIRL'S HANDS.
AND I'M, LIKE, "EW."
LIKE, THIS ISN'T OKAY.
- "I LIKE JIONNI
BETTER THAN ROGER
"BECAUSE JIONNI TOLD ME
HE LIKED ME IN MY DRESS
"AND HE'S CUTE AND SWEET.
MARRY ME."
- [bleep] OFF.
STUPID [bleep]ING SLUT.
THAT'S LIKE ME
GOING UP TO A GUY,
"HEY, I LIKE YOUR
[bleep]ING MUSCLES."
WHY ARE YOU GOING
TO A BAR AND HANGING OUT
WITH RANDOM GIRLS
WHEN YOU'RE ENGAGED
AND HAVING
A BABY ON THE WAY?
[phone buttons beeping]
[line ringing]
I CAN'T BREATHE.
[groaning]
- HELLO?
- HOW WAS HEMINGWAY'S?
- WHY? WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- WELL, DO YOU HAVE
ANYTHING TO TELL ME?
- NO.
- DID YOU SAY SOMETHING
TO A GIRL?
LIKE YOU'RE CHECKING HER OUT
AND YOU TOLD HER,
"NICE DRESS,
YOU LOOK GOOD."
- OH, YOU GOT ME.
- NO, I'M NOT KIDDING,
'CAUSE IT'S ALL OVER TWITTER
AND THERE'S PICTURES
OF HER ALL OVER YOU WITH,
LIKE, FIVE OTHER GIRLS.
AND YOU'RE, LIKE,
SMILING LIKE YOU WERE
SO [bleep]ING HAPPY
WITH THOSE GIRLS AROUND YOU.
- WELL, ME AND MY COUSIN
WERE IN THE PICTURES,
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
- NO, YOUR COUSIN WASN'T
IN THE PICTURE
BECAUSE I SEE THE PICTURE,
AND IT'S JUST YOU.
JUST ONE GUY WHO IS YOU
AND FIVE GIRLS AROUND HIM.
LIKE, WHY ARE YOU HAVING
CONVERSATIONS WITH THESE GIRLS
WHEN YOU'RE ENGAGED
AND I'M PREGNANT, SLEEPING?
- YOU'RE GETTING MAD AT ME
FOR SOMETHING--FOR NOTHING.
- NO, I'M NOT MAD AT YOU,
I'M REALLY DISAPPOINTED
AND I'M, LIKE, QUESTIONING
OUR ENGAGEMENT.
LIKE, ARE YOU READY?
'CAUSE IT SEEMS LIKE YOU
LIKE THIS [bleep]ING ATTENTION
WITH GIRLS.
- YOU'RE QUESTIONING
OUR ENGAGEMENT?
- YEAH, BECAUSE
YOU'RE GOING OUT
AND DOING THESE THINGS
THAT YOU KNOW I HATE.
- YOU WANNA
[bleep]ING SAY,
"OH, I DON'T KNOW ABOUT
OUR ENGAGEMENT,"
ESPECIALLY RIGHT NOW,
RIGHT HERE?
- BECAUSE I DON'T
LIKE HEARING--
- THAT'S [bleep] UP.
- I'M NOT [bleep] UP AT ALL.
I'M WATCHING OUT FOR MYSELF
AND MY BABY, SO THANKS.
- I THOUGHT YOU
WERE DIFFERENT THAN THAT.
I THOUGHT MAYBE
YOU WERE READY.
I THOUGHT MAYBE YOU WERE READY
TO BE A MOTHER AND A WIFE.
BUT MAYBE YOU'RE NOT.
YOU HEAR ONE LITTLE [bleep]ING
RUMOR AND YOU GO NUTS.
- THAT WAS MEAN.
- YOU'VE BEEN
SAYING THIS TO ME.
YOU SAID TO ME,
"I'M NOT READY."
AND I SAID,
"MAYBE YOU'RE NOT READY."
HELLO?
[phone clicks]
- [sniffling]
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- HE SAID I'M NOT READY
TO BE A MOM.
- I'M NOT GONNA BEAT
THIS [bleep]ING HORSE ANYMORE!
THIS SUCKER'S DEAD!
YOU'RE NOT
GONNA GET OVER IT.
I'M NOT GOING
TO APOLOGIZE.
STALEMATE.
- WHAT?
- IT'S A STALEMATE.
- WHAT THE [bleep]
IS A STALEMATE?