- CONGRATULATIONS IS IN ORDER
FOR YOU AND NICOLE.
- WHAT'S THE OVER-UNDER
ON HIM BEING 5 FOOT?
- 4 FOOT
IS MORE LIKE IT.
[laughter]
- NORMAL?
- MM-HMM.
- YOUR LITTLE BABY!
- YOU CREATED THAT.
DRUNK NIGHT.
- NO.
- * I DON'T CARE *
* I LOVE IT
* I DON'T CARE *
I LOVE IT *
* I DON'T CARE
* I DON'T CARE *
- OH, IT'S SO CUTE!
- IT'S MOVING.
[laughs]
[acoustic guitar music]
- * IT'S HOLDING THE WEIGHT
OF MY HOME *
- I'M SO EXCITED.
IT'S A LOT OF
INFORMATION TO TAKE IN.
LIKE, I JUST SAW MY BABY
TWISTING AND TWIRLING.
- BUT IT WAS LIKE A CELEBRATION
'CAUSE IT LOOKED FINE.
- MM-HMM.
- DID YOU SEE THE DINER?
- OH, RIGHT HERE.
MAYBE I'LL GET PANCAKES.
MMM.
EVERYTHING IS, LIKE,
SO REAL RIGHT NOW.
WE JUST SAW MY BABY
STRETCH AND KICK.
- NOW I'M SITTING
IN A DINER IN JERSEY CITY
WITH MY KNOCKED UP
BEST FRIEND.
- IT'S WEIRD, HOW THINGS WORK.
- [snorts]
- I THINK WE SHOULD
INVITE THE ROOMMATES OVER.
I DO HAVE IMPORTANT NEWS
TO TELL THEM.
- OH, YOU WANT TO TELL THEM?
- I THINK I SHOULD TELL THEM.
- PLACE WON'T BE
READY TILL SATURDAY.
- WELL, WE HAVE TIME ALL DAY
TOMORROW AND THEN THURSDAY.
- WHAT ABOUT DECORATIONS?
THERE IS, LIKE, NO PLACE
FOR DECORATIONS.
WE GOTTA GO TO
THE THRIFT STORE TOMORROW.
- WE JUST BOUGHT
A MILLION THINGS OF FABRIC.
- THAT'S NOT DECORATION.
- YEAH, WE COULD
MAKE A DECORATION.
- HOW YOU GONNA
MAKE A VASE OUT OF FABRIC?
- A WHAT?
- A "VAYSE."
- WHAT'S A "VAYSE"?
- A "VAAS."
- WHAT?
[dial tone,
dialing number]
[phone ringing]
- HELLO?
- HI, MAY I SPEAK TO ANTHONY?
- SPEAKING.
- I NEED SOMEONE TO HELP ME
TODAY WITH CURTAINS.
I AM REALLY EXCITED TO HAVE
MY SHORE-MATES AT THE HOUSE,
BUT I WANT THE HOUSE
TO BE DONE.
- ALL RIGHT,
SO I'LL SEE YOU AT 2:00.
- YOU ROCK. YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- ALL RIGHT, NO PROBLEM.
- BYE.
- NICOLE, YOU REALLY
GOTTA GET UP.
OUR HANDYMAN SOUNDED
LIKE A SEXY BLACK MAN.
JUST SAYING.
THANKS, BOO, FOR INVITING
EVERYONE OVER TOMORROW NIGHT.
THANKS FOR GETTING UP
AND HELPING.
I'M BASICALLY TAKING CONTROL
RIGHT NOW.
I WANT A NICE HOUSE,
AND I WANT THE ROOMMATES TO KNOW
THAT, LIKE, WE DECORATED IT.
YOU HAVE LEOPARD TAPE?
- I DO.
- REALLY?
WE'LL TAKE TEN EACH.
- OKAY.
- * SLEEP CHEAP
I LIKE THIS.
AT SLEEP CHEAP,
I GOT IT IN.
I BOUGHT A BAR SET,
A THREE-PIECE
ZEBRA OTTOMAN SET,
THREE RUGS,
A LEOPARD CHAIR,
AND A LEOPARD SHOE.
- I'LL GET IT THERE
FOR YOU TOMORROW
IF YOU REALLY NEED IT THAT BAD.
- OH!
I'M DOING WORK
RIGHT NOW.
BYE.
THANK YOU AGAIN.
WHAT A [bleep] ERRAND DAY.
[phone ringing]
- HELLO?
- PAULY?
- WHO'S THIS?
- HI, IT'S NICOLE.
- WHAT'S UP, GIRL?
- THE SHOREHOUSE ROOMMATES
ARE VERY IMPORTANT TO ME,
AND I FEEL LIKE THEY SHOULD
KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON.
- HELLO.
- HI, VIN.
IF YOU WANT TO, LIKE,
MAKE COOKIES OR, LIKE, A DISH,
THAT'S REALLY COOL.
- I'LL BRING A HOT POCKET.
[laughter]
- SHOULD I JUST
BRING RON RON JUICE INSTEAD?
- YEAH, BRING RON RON JUICE.
THEY'RE USED TO ME ALL PARTYING
AND DRUNK AND GOING CRAZY,
AND NOW I'M GONNA BE
A MOM AND A WIFE,
SO IT'S LIKE
TOTALLY, UM, 360.
SO YOU CAN MAKE IT?
- OF COURSE.
I'LL BE THERE.
- 'KAY, LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU.
- BYE.
- WOW, THIS IS EASIER
THAN I THOUGHT.
[dog yapping]
- SHH.
- ALL THE ROOMMATES
ARE COMING.
LIKE, EVEN PAULY.
- MIKE?
- I DIDN'T--NO.
I DIDN'T--I'M NOT INVITING HIM.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- YOU COULDN'T PAY ME ENOUGH
TO [bleep] DO THAT.
AND I'M NOT TALKING
TO MIKE ABOUT MY BUSINESS
'CAUSE HE'S NOT MY FRIEND.
[bell ringing]
- I HOPE OUR HANDYMAN'S HOT.
- WONDER WHAT HE LOOKS LIKE.
- HELLO, HOW YOU DOING?
- HI.
- ANTHONY.
- HI. JENNI.
- HOW YOU DOING?
NICE TO MEET YOU.
- HE DOESN'T SOUND BLACK.
- [speaks indistinctly]
- "SEXY BLACK MAN"?
- WHAT YOU'LL HELP WITH
IS DRAPING.
WE BASICALLY NEED
TO BE GUIDOFIED.
- OKAY.
DO YOU HAVE, LIKE,
THE BRACKETS
AND THE ATTACHMENTS
AND STUFF LIKE THAT
FOR ALL THIS STUFF OR--
- NO.
- YOU GOT A STAPLE GUN.
- I GOT A STAPLE GUN--
- WILL THAT WORK?
- YOU CAN'T STAPLE TO THIS.
HOW WE GONNA
STAPLE TO THIS?
- I HAVE NAIL GLUE.
- [laughs]
- YEAH.
- IT'S REALLY STURDY.
THANK GOD THAT NOW
WE HAVE A HANDYMAN,
SO HE CAN START DECORATING, ME
AND JENNI CAN DO THE PAINTING
AND JUST START GETTING THIS
PLACE, YOU KNOW, READY TO GO.
THIS IS WHAT I USED
TO WEAR IN SURGERIES,
WHEN I OPERATED
ON ANIMALS.
- I WAS JUST THINKING,
WHAT AM I GETTING PAID FOR THIS?
- HUGS AND KISSES.
I JUST STAPLED MY ASS.
- I WANT OUR HOUSE
TO BE A BARBIE'S DREAM HOUSE,
A BARBIE GUIDETTE DREAM HOUSE.
- WHAT'S IT SAY?
- "G."
FOR GARBAGE.
- THIS IS MY WAY
OF SEWING CURTAINS.
- I THINK NEXT TIME,
I'M GETTING A DECOR...
RATOR.
[laughter]
- YOU MEAN AN INTERIOR DESIGNER.
- YEAH.
OH, MY GOD, I THOUGHT I WAS
TALKING REALLY SMART.
- YOU'RE GONNA HAVE A LITTLE ZOO
IN HERE WHEN YOU'RE DONE.
- BASICALLY.
- THAT'S THE POINT.
- [laughs]
- PETA CAN'T GET MAD
AT OUR HOUSE.
- IT'S JUST CLOTH.
IT'S NOT LIKE A REAL ZEBRA.
UGH.
- ANTHONY,
TELL US A STORY.
- WHAT KIND OF STORY?
- A SEX STORY
THAT WENT WRONG.
- A SEX STORY.
- THAT WENT WRONG.
- YEAH.
- OH.
I GOT A CRAZY STORY
FOR YOU, ACTUALLY.
- WHOO-HOO!
- ME AND NICOLE LIKE
TO JOKE AROUND WITH PEOPLE,
AND WE LIKE TO SEE 'EM
BLUSH AND TURN RED.
- YEAH, EMBARRASS PEOPLE.
- THE WEIRD THING
ABOUT ANTHONY IS...
- HE LOVED IT.
- THIS GIRL--
THIS GIRL--
YOU KNOW, WE WERE [bleep],
AND, UH, ALL OF A SUDDEN...
YOU KNOW, ME AND MY FRIEND,
HE'S A PRETTY BIG DUDE TOO--
- DID HE [bleep]?
- ACTUALLY, SHE DID...
AS WE WERE [bleep].
- AND THAT'S WHEN
IT STARTED GETTING WEIRD.
- SHE GOES, "I WANT YOU
TO DO SOMETHING FOR ME.
I WANT YOU TO [bleep]."
- [bleep].
- I SAID, "NO."
I SAID I'LL [bleep].
THIS WAY, I DON'T HAVE TO SMELL
IT, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- I CAN'T STAND ANYMORE.
ME AND JIONNI ARE ENGAGED.
all: WHAT?
- CAN I SEE THE RING?
- DID YOU BUY IT?
[laughter]
- GREAT.
- NOW YOU YELL AT HIM.
TELL HIM TO [bleep] HURRY UP.
- WHAT ABOUT
THE CLUBBING DAYS?
I KNOW YOU GOT
CRAZY STORIES FROM THOSE.
- OKAY, WE'RE DONE.
- I KNOW, I PROBABLY MADE YOU
SICK WITH THAT STORY.
- NO.
- NOW YOU'RE LIKE,
"GET THIS GUY OUT OF HERE.
HE'S A [bleep] NUTCASE."
[clears throat]
ALL RIGHT.
SO WHAT'S THE DEAL WITH
THE MONEY NOW? SERIOUS.
- FRIDAY MORNING.
- I GOT KIDS.
DON'T FOOL AROUND
WITH MY MONEY.
I DON'T WANT TO HAVE
TO COME OVER HERE
LOOKING FOR YOU GUYS,
YOU KNOW?
- I FEEL LIKE HE JUST WANTS
TO TAKE US AWAY.
- YEAH.
- IN HIS DUNGEON.
- ALL RIGHT, LADIES,
HAVE A GOOD WEEK.
HOPE YOU HAVE A GOOD TIME
AT YOUR PARTY.
- I'M REALLY SCARED RIGHT NOW.
- ME TOO.
- ENJOY.
I'LL BE BY TO COLLECT.
- EW, HE GOT SO CREEPY.
- YEAH, LIKE, WEIRD.
[groans]
- I WANT TO GO TO SLEEP NOW.
- IT LOOKS
REALLY COOL IN HERE.
NOW I KNOW HOW
A HARDWORKING MAN FEELS.
- IF IT'S NOT GONNA BE DONE
TOMORROW, IT'LL BE DAMN CLOSE.
- ROME WASN'T
BUILT IN A DAY.
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED
TO SAY THAT.
MM.
- THE DRAPES AREN'T
EXACTLY WHAT I SAID,
BUT MAYBE WE JUST CAN'T GET 'EM
THE WAY WE WANT THEM.
- BEGGARS CAN'T BE CHOOSERS.
- MM-HMM.
- I'VE ALWAYS WANTED
TO SAY THAT ONE TOO.
JENNI, I'M GOING TO SLEEP.
GOOD NIGHT.
- * DON'T BE LAZY,
DON'T BE SHY *
* HOLD MY HAND
AND KISS THE NIGHT GOOD-BYE *
* OPEN YOUR EYES,
STAY BY MY SIDE *
- ARE YOU UP?
BOO, IT'S 11:00.
- I'M SO TIRED.
- OUR PICTURE GUY'S COMING,
SO WE HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT WE'RE WEARING.
READY?
ME AND NICOLE WANT BIG PAINTINGS
TO COVER UP THE UGLY WALL.
HEY, NICK.
- HI, ARE YOU JENNI?
- YEAH. COME IN, IT'S COLD.
- OH, THANKS.
- I FOUND NICK'S NUMBER
AT A DEPARTMENT STORE,
AND I CALLED HIM TO SEE IF
HE CAN PAINT PICTURES OF US.
THIS IS OUR PAINTER.
- HE LOOKS LIKE AN ARTIST.
- SO THESE ARE
JUST SOME OF MY FRIENDS.
WE LIKE TO GO TO THRIFT STORES
AND FIND, LIKE, OUTFITS,
AND THEN I PAINT THEM.
- SEXY.
- VERY SEXY.
[laughs]
AND THEN--
- YOU TAKE A PICTURE OF THEM
AND THEN YOU DRAW IT?
- YEAH.
- 'CAUSE WE THOUGHT WE'D HAVE TO
SIT THERE FOR,
LIKE, THREE HOURS.
- IT'S A LITTLE BIT HARD
TO SIT STILL FOR AN HOUR.
- TWO PICTURES OF US
LOOKING MAD HARD
WOULD DEFINITELY MAKE
THE APARTMENT.
- HEY, PUPPY.
[clicks tongue]
SATURDAY MORNING'S OKAY?
both: YES.
- WONDERFUL, GREAT. WELL, IT
WAS NICE TO MEET BOTH OF YOU.
- IT'S GONNA LOOK SICK.
- I'M GONNA GET CHANGED.
READY?
- YEP.
TONIGHT, THE ROOMMATES ARE
COMING OVER, SO ME AND JENNI
HAVE A BUSY, BUSY DAY
AHEAD OF US WITH SHOPPING...
DOES DIET MEAN
IT'S NON-CAFFEINE,
OR IT'S JUST
LESS CAFFEINE?
- YEAH, IT'S LESS.
- I HAVE NO IDEA HOW
THE ROOMMATES ARE GONNA REACT.
I'M GONNA TELL THEM
I'M ENGAGED FIRST,
BUT I ALSO WANT A COOL WAY
OF SAYING I'M PREGNANT.
- WE WANT TO MAKE, LIKE,
A REALLY, REALLY NICE CAKE.
- OKAY.
- BUT WE WANT TO PUT
A SPECIAL MESSAGE ON IT.
- I'M PREGNANT.
DIG IN!
JENNI, LOOK!
- OH, NO.
- I LOOK UP, AND ALL THE DRAPES
ARE FALLING DOWN.
WHAT THE [bleep]
ARE WE GONNA DO NOW?
BECAUSE NOW THE HOUSE
LOOKS LIKE [bleep].
NOT IN THE MOOD
TO DO THIS RIGHT NOW.
LET'S CANCEL.
- IT'S GONNA
TAKE TWO HOURS
JUST TO CLEAN UP
THIS TAPE OFF THE WALL.
- IT'S NOT WORTH IT.
I DON'T WANT THEM
OVER ANYMORE.
- IT LOOKS HORRIBLE.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- BUZZKILL.
- OW!
[pained groan]
[muffled]
HOW DOES THAT LOOK?
- EH.
I'M GONNA LOOK ONLINE
AND SEE IF THERE'S MORE
HANDY PEOPLE AROUND HERE.
"HANDYMAN."
I FEEL LIKE
I'M LOOKING UP PROSTITUTES.
ALL RIGHT, POOP, I FOUND
FOUR OTHER HANDYMANS.
- START CALLING.
SEE WHO CAN GET HERE
THE FASTEST.
[burps]
[phone ringing]
- HELLO?
- UM, ARE YOU A HANDYMAN?
- I'M VERY HANDY, MAN.
- EW.
ALL RIGHT, ONE MORE.
[phone ringing]
- HELLO.
- HI, ARE YOU A HANDYMAN?
- I AM A HANDYMAN.
- OH, MY GOD,
ARE YOU AVAILABLE RIGHT NOW?
THIS ONE GUY
SOUNDS PROFESSIONAL,
SO HE'S NOT GONNA
TALK ABOUT [bleep].
[bell rings]
YAY!
HI.
- HELLO, HOW ARE YOU?
I'M BRIAN THE HANDYMAN.
- YES.
- HOW ARE YOU?
HI, PUPPY--
OH, [bleep].
- NOEL!
- [laughs]
JESUS.
[laughs]
- YOU ARE GONNA GET YOUR ASS
HANDED TO YOU.
OUR DAY'S GETTING WORSE.
- HE DOESN'T SEEM CREEPY.
- UH, HI, HOW ARE YOU?
IT'S...INCREDIBLY PINK.
- THEY WERE DRAPED
ALL THE WAY UP TOP,
AND NOW THEY JUST SAG.
- SO YOU JUST WANNA
HANG THE DRAPES, RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- JUST KINDA MAKE IT NICE?
- NICE AND DROOPY.
BASICALLY, IT'S THE LAST HOUR
BEFORE THE ROOMMATES GET HERE.
I DON'T KNOW IF
WE'RE GONNA PULL THIS OFF.
LET'S DO THIS.
OUR CAKE'S HERE.
- YEAH, THEY'LL
GET THE MESSAGE.
NO!
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
- REALLY?
NOTHING'S GOING RIGHT RIGHT NOW.
[container plops]
- [gasps]
- WHO PUT
THE SPICE RACK UP HERE?
- YOU.
- SHUT UP.
- OH, MY GOD,
SO MUCH BETTER.
- SO I'LL GET OUT OF HERE.
ENJOY YOUR PARTY.
- YOU'RE A LIFESAVER.
- LOVE YOU.
- LOVE YOU BACK.
- * LET'S LIVE IT UP,
TURN IT UP *
* TIME IS FEELING RIGHT
* NO MORE WAITING
[doorbell rings]
- UH-OH.
- WILL YOU GET IT?
- YOU GET IT.
- I'M COOKING MY GREEN BEANS.
- [bleep] YOUR GREEN BEANS.
GO ANSWER THE DOOR.
- WHY DO YOU BOSS ME AROUND?
- I'M NOT BOSSING YOU AROUND,
BUT I'M TRYING TO TAKE OUT--
- YOU ALWAYS BOSS ME AROUND.
- ALL RIGHT.
- "DO THIS, DO THAT,
RAH, RAH, RAH."
HELLO?
- SNOOKS?
- PAULY!
- [laughs]
HELL YEAH.
- HI!
- HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD, HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD TO SEE YOU.
- WELCOME TO MY HOUSE.
- THIS IS THE PLACE, HUH?
- YEAH.
I'M SO HAPPY TO SEE PAULY
BECAUSE PAULY ALWAYS
HAS A SMILE ON HIS FACE.
LIKE, YOU KNOW, I FEEL LIKE
I'M BACK AT THE SHORE.
- YO, I CALLED THE ANIMAL PRINT.
- IT'S NOT DONE.
- OBVIOUSLY.
- CALLED IT.
THE STYLE OF THIS HOUSE IS,
LIKE, AN ART DECO.
NO.
[laughs]
IT'S JUST
SNOOKI AND JENNI.
IT'S JUST ANIMAL PRINT
AFTER ANIMAL PRINT.
I DON'T THINK
THERE'S ANY MORE ANIMAL PRINT
LEFT IN JERSEY RIGHT NOW.
IT'S ALL IN THIS HOUSE.
- WE GOT A NICE CAKE
FOR DESSERT.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING COOKING?
[laughs]
- IT'S THE FIRST TIME ON MY OWN!
I HAVE TO LEARN SOMETIME.
- HOW DO YOU KNOW
HOW TO DO THIS?
[doorbell rings]
- HELLO?
- HEY. HEY.
WE'RE HERE TO DROP OFF
THE FURNITURE.
- OH!
OUR FURNITURE IS HERE.
- YAY, OUR FURNITURE'S HERE.
- SAY WHAT?
NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
I'M UNWRAPPING FURNITURE,
I'M PUTTING TOGETHER CHAIRS.
I DON'T KNOW,
THIS WASN'T WHAT I EXPECTED.
THAT'S YOUR COFFIN WHEN
YOU PASS AWAY, GOD FORBID.
- OOH!
- I KNOW.
- [laughs]
- COULD I FIT IN THERE?
- COURSE YOU DO.
- LET ME SEE.
- THAT'S GREAT.
- WHEN I DIE, I WANNA DIE
IN A ZEBRA COFFIN.
- [chuckles]
- WHY YOU LAUGHING?
- JUST TAKE THE OTTOMAN.
YOU DON'T EVEN NEED
TO BUY A COFFIN.
- I KNOW, BUT THEN THE BUGS
CAN GET IN AND EAT ME.
- OH, THIS IS GREAT.
- R.I.P.
- GOD REST YOUR SOUL.
[laughter]
- IF SHE TOOK HER HEELS OFF,
SHE'D BE ABLE TO FIT
ALL THE WAY IN.
- YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO COME UP
LIKE A MUMMY, LIKE THIS.
- I'LL TAKE IT.
- [droning]
ARISE FROM THE DEAD.
- DUDE, I REALLY WANT
MY COFFIN LIKE THIS.
- [laughs]
- THERE'S MORE
SNOOKI &amp; JWOWW ON THE WAY,
AND IT STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
- WHAT THE HELL IS THIS PLACE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
WAIT, WAIT, IS THIS IT?
I WAS EXPECTING IT
TO BE DIFFERENT.
- OH, YEAH, NEW RUG.
YEAH, BUDDY, NEW RUG.
[doorbell rings]
- YAY!
- OH, WE'RE AT
THE WRONG APARTMENT.
- I DON'T KNOW.
- HELLO!
- AAH!
- OH, MY GOD!
YOU JUST WALK INTO MY HOUSE.
[indistinct chatter]
- HI.
- HI, YOU LOOK CUTE.
- THANK YOU.
- OH, MY GOD, HOW THE HELL--
- OH, IT'S DEENA.
- 'SUP? HOW ARE YOU?
- SAM.
- GOOD TO SEE YOU.
- WELCOME TO MY HOME.
- I KNOW, IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
- I JUST MOVED IN.
- OH, I BROUGHT
A HOUSEWARMING GIFT.
- WINE!
- YUM.
- BOXED.
- SO I'M DRINKING
CRANBERRY JUICE
OUT OF A WINE GLASS
RIGHT NOW,
BECAUSE IF I WASN'T
DRINKING ANYTHING,
EVERYBODY WOULD BE LIKE, YOU
KNOW, "WHY AREN'T YOU DRINKING?"
- WHOSE IS THIS?
- NICOLE.
- WHAT KIND?
- NEW.
- OH.
- IT DIDN'T LOOK LIKE WINE.
- NO.
- IT LOOKED
LIKE CRANBERRY JUICE.
- IN A WINE GLASS.
- YEAH.
- WE HAVE REALLY GOOD DESSERTS
FOR TONIGHT.
- YOU HAD ME AT DESSERT.
- SO WHO WE WAITING FOR,
TWO BOYS?
- YEAH, IT'S JUST
ME AND ALL THE CHICKS.
- HELLO?
- I KNOW, YOU POOR THING.
- IT'S ALL GOOD.
- OH, [bleep].
- POPULAR MUSIC PLAYED
BY A MODERN BAND.
[doorbell rings]
- WHO IS IT?
- IT'S VINNY.
- HEY.
I'M EXCITED TO SEE MY ROOMMATES
IN A DIFFERENT SCENARIO.
WHAT'S UP, BRO?
I LOVE YOUR NEW HOUSE.
- THANKS, MAN.
JUST GOT IT.
- FIRST TIME
WE ALL GET TOGETHER
AND JUST MAKE FUN OF EACH OTHER
IS ALWAYS THE BEST TIME.
WHOA, WHERE ARE WE GOING?
- THAT'S MY BOYFRIEND.
- OH, THEY'RE GOING
IN THE SMUSH.
- THEY'RE GOING
IN YOUR ROOM.
- SNOOKS, CAN WE USE
YOUR BED REAL QUICK?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- CAN WE USE YOUR BED?
- NO!
NOT MY SMUSH!
[laughter]
- NOW WE'RE JUST
WAITING FOR RONALD.
- WHERE'S MIKE?
- HE COULDN'T MAKE IT.
- MIKE COULDN'T MAKE IT.
- RONNIE!
- RON!
- SAM, YOU GO GET IT.
- AWKWARD.
- ARE YOU GUYS TOGETHER?
- BETTER LATE THAN NEVER.
- OH, HEY, RON!
- I FEEL LIKE
IT'S ALWAYS AWKWARD
WITH RON AND SAM
IF THEY'RE NOT TOGETHER.
- I LOOK AT RON AND SAM
LIKE A MOOD RING.
- [gasps]
I LOVE MOOD RINGS.
- YEAH, BUT YOU DON'T WANT
THAT [bleep] TO TURN BLACK.
- OH, YEAH.
- HEY.
- HI.
- DID YOU SKIN A COW
FOR THOSE CURTAINS OR--
- [laughs]
- DO YOU LIKE OUR PLACE?
- IT'S VERY SNOOKI AND JENNI.
- IT'S VERY--
IT'S CREEPY, BUT...
- [laughs]
- IT'S CUTE.
- IT'S VERY...CHIC,
SHOULD I SAY?
- CREEPY.
- BOYS WILL BE BOYS.
JEN, ARE YOU READY?
- I'M SITTING NEXT
TO MY BOYFRIEND.
TUCK ME IN, BABE.
[sighs]
- SORRY.
- THIS IS AMAZING.
WHO HAD EVER
THOUGHT WE'D BE
AT SNOOKI AND JENNI'S
HOUSE FOR DINNER?
- WHAT THE HELL
DID YOU DO WITH NICOLE?
NICOLE IS COOKING,
CLEANING...
THIS IS, LIKE, [bleep] THAT
I'VE NEVER SEEN FROM NICOLE.
[bleep] HELL IS
FREEZING OVER RIGHT NOW.
YO, THIS ACTUALLY
LOOKS EDIBLE.
OH, [bleep], LOOK AT THAT.
- WOW.
- WOW, IT'S MEATBALLS.
- IT'S REAL FOOD!
- SO WHAT'S NEW
WITH EVERYBODY?
- ME AND VINNY BEEN HAVING
AN OPEN RELATIONSHIP.
- YEAH.
- I BEEN LETTING HIM BANG
OTHER CHICKS AND [bleep]...
- IT'S BEEN WORKING OUT.
- AS LONG AS HE
COMES HOME TO ME.
- WHAT ABOUT YOU AND CHRIS?
- REALLY GOOD.
- REALLY?
- SHE'S IN LOVE.
- MM-HMM.
- I THINK HE'S REALLY GOOD.
- I GOT A GIRLFRIEND TOO.
- REALLY?
- YOU DO?
- NO.
[laughter]
- 'CAUSE I WAS ABOUT
TO BE LIKE, "YEAH, RIGHT."
- THANK YOU, GUYS, FOR COMING.
IT MEANS THE WORLD TO US.
- NAH, THANKS FOR HAVING US.
THIS IS DOPE.
THIS IS REAL DOPE.
- YOU KNOW IT MEANS A LOT TO US,
LIKE, LIVING ON
OUR OWN AND STUFF LIKE THIS,
BUT, UM, THE REAL REASON WHY
I INVITED YOU GUYS HERE...
- UH-OH.
- IS BECAUSE ME AND JIONNI
ARE ENGAGED.
all: WHAT?
- CONGRATULATIONS!
- AWW.
- OH, MY GOD!
- OH, YAY!
WHEN DID HE--WAIT.
- YEAH.
- I WAS EXPECTING A DINNER,
WE SEE THE HOUSE,
NOT EXPECT SNOOKI TO BE
ENGAGED RIGHT NOW.
I'M DJ'ING THE WEDDING.
- LET'S GIVE A CHEERS.
- CONGRATULATIONS, SNOOK,
BY THE WAY.
- YEAH.
- THANK YOU.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU CAME A LONG WAY.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE GETTING MARRIED.
- I CANNOT BELIEVE
THAT YOU GUYS ARE ENGAGED.
- YOU DOMESTICATED HER!
- DO YOU HAVE A DATE YET?
- LIKE, A YEAR OR TWO.
NOT ANYTHING SOON.
- NICOLE GETTING ENGAGED
IS CRAZY TO ME
JUST BECAUSE, LIKE,
I FEEL LIKE SHE HASN'T
REALLY KNOWN JIONNI
FOR THAT LONG.
AND THEY'RE GETTING
ENGAGED ALREADY?
THAT'S, LIKE,
SERIOUS [bleep], I FEEL.
- I'M A LITTLE
UPSET ABOUT THIS.
- ARE YOU?
- YOU THINK TWO YEARS IS
A LONG ENOUGH TIME
TO MARRY SOMEBODY
AND SPEND THE REST
OF YOUR DAYS WITH?
- YOU KNOW THAT'S ONE PERSON FOR
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE, RIGHT?
RIGHT, SNOOK?
- YOU KNOW THAT'S ONE PENIS
FOR THE REST
OF YOUR LIFE, RIGHT?
- I LOVE HIS PENIS.
- OOH.
- JIONNI WAS A ONE-NIGHT STAND
OF NICOLE.
LIKE, ENGAGED MEANS THE REST
OF YOUR LIFE TYPE OF [bleep].
YOU'RE GONNA DO IT TO SOMEBODY
YOU [bleep] ONE-NIGHT STOOD?
THAT'S CRAZY.
HOW DOES HE FEEL ABOUT IT?
- HE'S SO EXCITED.
- DID JIONNI FINISH SCHOOL YET?
- NO.
- CAN I SEE THE RING?
DID SHE BUY IT?
- [laughs]
STOP.
[laughter]
- GREAT.
THIS IS NOT SOMETHING
TO BUST MY BALLS ABOUT,
AND THE FACT THAT JENNI IS,
LIKE, CHIMING IN WITH THEM--
I'M LIKE,
"BITCH, REALLY?"
- JUST GET IT OVER WITH,
DO IT.
YOU GUYS ARE GONNA
BE DIVORCED SOON ANYWAY.
- WOW.
- I KIND OF REGRET
EVEN INVITING
THE ROOMMATES OVER
BECAUSE THEY'RE JUST
TREATING IT LIKE A JOKE.
- OH, BOY.
- I'M NOT EVEN EXCITED
TO TELL THEM I'M PREGNANT
BECAUSE OF THE REACTION I GOT
SAYING I'M ENGAGED.
- AWKWARD.
[chuckles]
- UGH, WORST TIME OF MY LIFE.
- WOW, IT IS FANCY.
- WHAT'S IT SAY?
- "BY THE WAY,
I'M PREGNANT."
- HOLY [bleep]! WHAT?
- OH, MY GOD.
- YOU'RE PREGNANT?
- OH, [bleep].
both: IT'S NOT YOURS!
- I FEEL LIKE ROGER JUST DOESN'T
KNOW WHEN ENOUGH IS ENOUGH.
- I'VE HAD CHLAMYDIA
FOUR TIMES.
- HE'S RIGHT NEXT TO MY DAD.
- WHAT, ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
- ALL RIGHT.
JIONNI WANTS
TO CHALLENGE ME.
I'M GONNA BREAK THIS KID LIKE
A TWIG, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?