- SO WHAT'’S THE CONCLUSION?
- WE'’RE GONNA TAKE IT!
- I HAVE A NICOLE
THAT'’S PREGNANT AND ENGAGED.
I DON'’T KNOW WHAT
I'’M GETTING MYSELF INTO.
- JENNI, I'’M PUTTING IN
AN OFFICIAL REQUEST
FOR JIONNI'’S BACHELOR PARTY.
- NO.
I DON'’T WANT NO DIRTY SKANK
GRINDING ON HIM.
- WHY ARE YOU
COOL WITH IT THEN?
- HE WOULD LEAVE ME
IF I WAS LIKE THAT.
- [laughs]
- ♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT ♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
♪ I LOVE IT, I LOVE IT ♪
♪ I LOVE IT ♪
♪ I DON'’T CARE ♪
- I DON'’T MIND
A BACHELOR PARTY.
I'’M TALKING ABOUT
[bleep] ASS IN THEIR FACE.
- NO, JIONNI SAID
STRIPPERS MAKE HIM THROW UP.
- JENNI THINKS THAT SOME GIRL
COULD CONVINCE ME
THAT IT'’S OKAY TO CHEAT.
- RIGHT, LIKE EVERY OTHER GUY,
IT'’S LIKE THE HANGOVER.
HE THINKS THAT I'’M THAT...
- HE NEVER SAID--
- NO STRIPPERS.
- I NEVER SAID, "CHEAT."
I SAID, "DISRESPECT."
- LIKE I GOTTA
SMELL THE WHORE ON YOU.
- TO WHO? TO WHO?
- TO ME.
- SHE DOESN'’T OWE YOU
A DIME OF RESPECT.
- YOU DO!
- SO, YOU'’RE TALKING ABOUT ME?
- YEAH.
- I OWE YOU RESPECT
TO NOT GO THERE.
- NO, NOT HAVE
A GIRL BE ON YOU.
- OH, MY GOD, JENNI,
THAT'’S JUST HOW IT WORKS
AT A BACHELOR PARTY.
THAT'’S JUST WHAT HAPPENS.
- THAT'’S WHY YOU DON'’T GO.
- I DON'’T--I'’M NOT DOING A STRIP
CLUB, JUST TO LET YOU KNOW.
- SEE?
JIONNI DOESN'’T
LIKE STRIPPERS, SO...
- ALL GUYS SAY
THEY DON'’T LIKE STRIPPERS.
- NO, HE REALLY
DOESN'’T LIKE STRIPPERS.
- I DON'’T WANNA TALK ABOUT
THE BACHELOR PARTY ANYMORE.
TODAY'’S JENNI'’S BIRTHDAY.
LET'’S HAVE FUN.
- I AGREE WITH THAT,
I SECOND THAT.
- I THINK STRIPPERS
ARE [bleep] DISGUSTING.
- THANK YOU.
- I MEAN, THEY'’RE SLUTS.
- [bleep] PROSTITUTES.
- YEAH.
- YAY.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO ME.
- BABE,
I JUST GOT BUTTERFLIES!
'’CAUSE I'’M EXCITED
YOU'’RE HERE.
DO YOU GET BUTTERFLIES?
- NO. SHE WON'’T EVEN HAVE SEX
WITH ME. YOU KIDDING ME?
I TRY TO HUMP THIS GIRL,
LIKE, FIVE TIMES A DAY.
- HOW MANY TIMES
DO YOU MASTURBATE THEN?
- A LOT.
- THAT SUCKS.
- LET'’S BE--
LET'’S BE HONEST ABOUT IT.
- ♪ HAPPY BIRTHDAY
TO MY BEST FRIEND ♪
- SO WE'’RE ALL GOING OUT FOR
DINNER FOR JENNI'’S BIRTHDAY,
AND IT'’S REALLY,
REALLY NICE.
IT'’S LIKE A NICE
DOUBLE DATE.
- LAST NIGHT,
I HAD FULL-BLOWN ANXIETY
THINKING 27 WAS
THE END OF MY LIFE.
- SHE HAS THE MOST RIDICULOUS
THOUGHTS OF ANYBODY I KNOW.
- IT'’S ALL RIGHT.
- MY BIOLOGICAL
CLOCK'’S TICKING.
- SO IS THAT SAYING
YOU WANT A BABY?
- I DON'’T WANT
TO BE AN OLD MOM.
- I'’M GONNA BE AN OLD DAD.
I'’M COOL WITH IT.
I WOULD'’VE BEEN IN NO POSITION
TO HAVE A KID AT 27.
I WOULDN'’T HAVE.
BOTTOM LINE.
- WHAT ABOUT--WHAT ABOUT 24?
- AT 24 WOULD I HAVE?
NO [bleep] WAY, DUDE.
- THAT WAS MY PARENTS.
- BUT WE CAN'’T GO BY THAT.
- DID YOU--DID YOU
EXPERIENCE LIFE YET?
DID YOU EXPERIENCE
ALL THAT LIFE HAD TO OFFER?
- I EXPERIENCED EVERYTHI--
- DID YOU SOW YOUR WILD OATS,
SO TO SPEAK?
- WE'’RE EXPERIENCING IT
RIGHT NOW.
- I EXPERIENCED EVERYTHING
I HAD TO EXPERIENCE.
I WENT AWAY TO COLLEGE.
- IT'’S COLLEGE.
IT DOESN'’T COUNT. DOESN'’T COUNT.
WHEN YOU LOOK BACK ON IT,
THAT'’S WHEN YOU CAN SAY
YOU'’VE EXPERIENCED EVERYTHING
YOU HAD TO EXPERIENCE.
YOU'’RE NOT
LOOKING BACK ON IT.
YOU'’RE LIVING IN THE PRESENT
RIGHT NOW, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
[laughs]
- NO...
YOU MAKE CHOI--IT'’S--
I HAD A FAKE I.D. FOREVER,
I WENT OUT AND DID CRAZY THI--
YOU KNOW, LIKE, I WAS...
- BUT DOES THAT DEFINE
LIVING LIFE TO THE FULLEST?
KNOW WHAT I MEAN? LIKE, REALLY?
- ROG, I WENT CRAZY.
- I'’M A BALL-BREAKER BY NATURE.
I'’M JUST A BALL-BREAKER.
AND JIONNI AND I ARE KIND OF
HAVING A NEW FRIENDSHIP,
AND IT'’S JUST, LIKE, THIS
PERFECT CANVAS TO MAKE FUN OF.
SO, WHERE DO YOU
SEE YOURSELF IN FIVE YEARS?
- HE WANTS A SPEEDBOAT.
- REALLY?
- I WANNA RACE, TO BE HONEST,
BUT SHE WON'’T LET ME RACE.
- BOATS?
- YEAH.
- THERE'’S A THING
CALLED "BOAT RACING"?
- MAN'’S GOT
HIS PRIORITIES IN CHECK.
HE'’S HAVING A KID,
AND HE WANTS TO RACE BOATS.
THANK GOD YOU'’RE HANDSOME, BRO,
'’CAUSE YOU'’RE NOT VERY BRIGHT.
- [laughs]
- [chuckling]
- WHAT'’S THE MATTER?
IT'’S JUST IDEAS.
IT AIN'’T GONNA HAPPEN.
- I'’M KIDDING.
- EVERYBODY'’S A DREAMER.
RIGHT?
- IS SHE MAD? ARE YOU MAD?
- YEAH, IT'’S ANNOYING.
- I'’M KIDDING.
- I'’M IGNORING EVERYTHING
THAT ROGER'’S SAYING
JUST BECAUSE
HE'’S INTERROGATING JIONNI,
AND YOU KNOW,
IT'’S ANNOYING, AND I'’M--
I'’M KIND OF
GETTING DEFENSIVE FOR JIONNI.
LIKE, DON'’T [bleep]
TALK TO MY MAN LIKE THAT.
YOU'’RE ANNOYING.
- I'’M NOT GONNA
GET A BOAT.
- THEN STOP TALKING ABOUT IT.
- ALL RIGHT.
[clears throat]
- [laughs]
- ♪ OOMPA, DOOMPA,
DOOMPITY DOO ♪
- [laughs]
OH, MY GOD, HE DID NOT.
YOU DON'’T SING
THE OOMPA LOOMPA SONG.
- OW, MOVE UP!
[laughter]
DOING? YOU BIG GOOF.
- YOU'’RE CRUNCHING HIM.
- YOU DON'’T HAVE ENOUGH ROOM?
- [laughs]
- WE SHOULD'’VE GOTTEN
MAGIC CANDLES.
ALL RIGHT, COME OVER HERE.
- ALL RIGHT, JENNI, BLOW IT OUT.
- ALL RIGHT, BLOW IT OUT.
- OH, MY GOD, THANK YOU.
- VERY COOL.
- YUM.
- MAKE A WISH.
- [blows]
[blows]
- DOES IT COME TRUE '’CAUSE YOU
DIDN'’T GET IT ALL IN ONE BREATH?
[applause]
- YAY.
- YES.
- CAN I HAVE YOUR BOOBS?
- OOH...
I JUST ATE MYSELF.
- CAN I HAVE SOME
OF THAT STRAWBERRY?
- YOU COULD PRACTICE.
PRACTICE FOR HAVING A KID, DUDE.
THE AIRPLANE.
DO THE AIRPLANE.
- OH, I DON'’T LIKE THAT.
IT'’S ANNOYING.
- HE'’S THE SAME SIZE AS A KID.
COME ON.
- [laughs]
- [imitates airplane]
- WHY'’D YOU JUST TAKE IT?
- GET OUTTA HERE.
[laughs]
- LET'’S BE HONEST
ABOUT IT FOR A MINUTE.
IF WE HAD A KID, YOU'’D BE
THE SAME SIZE AS OUR KID.
[laughs]
- YOU KNOW WHAT? I SWEAR TO GOD.
- I DEFINITELY FEEL LIKE
ROGER [bleep] WITH JIONNI
ALL THE TIME.
- OH, HE DOES?
- YEAH, A LITTLE BIT.
- OUTTA LOVE.
- JIONNI DOESN'’T GIVE A [bleep].
NO, I KNOW.
BUT I'’M JUST LIKE, "SHUT UP.
HE'’S PERFECT."
- YOU'’RE A BIG BULLY.
- [laughs]
- I KNOW.
- I'’VE HAD ASSEMBLIES ABOUT YOU.
[laughter]
- I HAD A BIGGER BOWEL MOVEMENT
THAN YOU THIS MORNING.
[laughter]
- ROGER!
- I'’M LEAVING, NICOLE.
- YELL AT HIM.
- YOU'’RE FUNNY, ROG.
- [laughs]
- SEE THE BABY MOVING AROUND?
- EWW!
- OH, IT'’S SO CUTE.
- OH, I'’M GONNA THROW UP.
- HOW AM I ABOUT TO CRY,
AND YOU'’RE, LIKE,
GONNA THROW UP?
- I'’M GETTING YOU
PINK POLKA DOT WALLPAPER.
- ME AND NICOLE NEED DRAPES.
WE NEED SOMETHING
TO COVER THE WALLS.
SO WE'’RE GONNA
GO TO A FEW STORES,
AND, LIKE, REALLY
DO WORK FOR THE HOUSE.
- WELCOME TO NEW JERSEY
DECORATING.
- I'’M EXCITED.
- I WANT WALLPAPER
LIKE ZEBRA
ANIMAL-PRINT WALLPAPER
IN MY ROOM,
SO IT'’S JUST
MORE GAUDY AND OUTRAGEOUS.
'’CAUSE THEN I'’LL REALLY
FEEL LIKE IT'’S MY HOME.
I LIKE THIS.
IT MATCHES MY TATTOO.
- OH, MY GOODNESS.
- I DEFINITELY
LIKE THE BLACK SHINY...
- I WANT ANIMAL PRINT.
I WANT IT VERY TACKY.
- [laughs]
- YEAH, IF I COULD
HAVE THAT BUT BLACK,
IT WOULD BE BEAUTIFUL.
- I LIKE THAT SOUND.
- YOU LIKE THESE TWO TOGETHER?
- MM-HMM.
I LOVE THAT.
- MISSION ACCOMPLISHED?
- YEAH.
- GRAND TOTAL...
$1,132.40.
- OH, MY GOD.
I CAN BUY, LIKE,
A LOUIS VUITTON BAG FOR THAT.
AND I, LIKE, [bleep] MYSELF
WHEN I BUY THOSE TYPE OF BAGS.
- COULD YOU ASK THEM
FOR A BIGGER DISCOUNT?
- OKAY.
- OKAY?
- [laughs]
- WHY NOT?
- PLEASE.
- ALL RIGHT.
- YOU DO THE SAD LIP,
AND THEN YOU DO, LIKE,
THE BATTING OF THE EYES,
AND THOSE--MOSTLY WORKS.
UNLESS YOU'’RE A GRENADE.
- SO, IT'’S 642 FOR THE BOTH.
- I LOVE YOU!
- OKAY, THANKS FOR COMING IN.
- THANK YOU.
- GOOD LUCK WITH THE NEW HOUSE.
- THANK YOU. BYE.
DO YOU LIKE COW?
- COW SKIN?
- YEAH.
- OOH, I LIKE THAT.
EVERY STORE
SHOULD HAVE ANIMAL PRINT,
BECAUSE IF THEY DON'’T,
THEN IT'’S A REALLY BORING STORE,
AND I WOULD NEVER GO IN IT.
JENNI.
- YEAH?
- LOOK.
- I'’M REALLY
GETTING ANNOYED AT, LIKE,
THE BABY/WEDDING FEVER GOING--
- I LOVE IT!
- YEAH...
- [giggles]
- THANKS FOR YELLING
IN MY [bleep] EAR.
[sighs]
OH...
NOTHING HAPPENED.
I'’M OKAY.
SORRY.
- OH, MY GOD, I REALLY
HAVE TO FREAKIN'’ POOP.
ALL I'’M THINKING IS,
"OH, MY GOD,
I HAVE TO POOP SO BAD,"
AND YOU SHOULDN'’T
HOLD YOUR POOP IN,
ESPECIALLY WHEN
YOU'’RE PREGGERS,
BECAUSE TECHNICALLY,
I'’M POOPING FOR TWO PEOPLE,
SO WHEN YOU
HOLD IN YOUR POOP,
YOU'’RE JUST BACKING UP
YOUR KID'’S POOP.
AND I FEEL LIKE
THAT'’S NOT HEALTHY.
I'’M SORRY,
BUT I REALLY HAVE TO POOP.
- JUST GO,
'’CAUSE YOU'’RE ANNOYING ME NOW.
[laughs]
- IT KEEPS DOING THIS.
- IT'’S PUCKERING.
JUST GO.
UGH...
- BYE.
OH, MY GOD,
THERE'’S ALREADY POOP IN THERE.
OH, MY GOD.
- WHAT'’S THE PROBLEM?
- THERE'’S ALREADY
POOP IN THE TOILET.
- THERE IS?
- SO, I WALK
INTO THE BATHROOM,
AND THERE'’S
ALREADY [bleep] TURDS
JUST CHILLIN'’
IN THE TOILET,
SO, I'’M LIKE, "I AM NOT POOPING
IN THIS PLACE."
- WHY DON'’T YOU JUST
FLUSH THE TOILET?
- BECAUSE IT'’S WEIRD.
AND THERE'’S LITTLE TURDS
LOOKING AT ME.
- THINK YOU GOT
POOP PARTICLES ON YOU?
- YEAH,
AND I TOUCHED THE LIGHT.
- ALL RIGHT, I THINK WE'’RE READY
TO GET OUR STUFF, MISTER.
- YES.
- THANK YOU.
- THANKS A LOT.
I APPRECIATE YOUR BUSINESS.
- HAVE A NICE DAY.
[dance music]
- I'’M EXCITED FOR TONIGHT.
- I'’M EXCITED
FOR THE SEX MUSEUM.
YOU THINK THEY'’RE
ACTUALLY GONNA DO SEX?
- I DON'’T KNOW
EXACTLY WHAT IT IS.
- IS THAT LEGAL?
- I FEEL LIKE A BREAK AWAY
FROM WHAT WE'’VE BEEN DOING
IS MUCH-NEEDED.
WE WANNA DO THE SEX MUSEUM,
WE WANNA GO TO NINJA DINNER.
- JUST TO GET OUTTA JERSEY CITY
FOR A LITTLE BIT,
AND GO TO NEW YORK CITY.
I'’M REALLY EXCITED.
- I CAN'’T WAIT.
MUSEUM OF SEX.
- OH, THIS IS A STORE.
- REALLY GLAD YOU GUYS ARE HERE.
WELCOME TO THE MUSEUM OF SEX.
- OOH, WHAT IS THAT,
ANAL BEADS?
SO, WE GET
TO THE SEX MUSEUM,
AND THAT'’S EXACTLY
WHAT IT'’S ABOUT--SEX.
A LITTLE SHOCKED.
- EWW!
THERE'’S SPRINKLES ON IT.
- [laughs]
- THAT MUST REALLY HURT
WHEN YOU PUT IT IN YOUR [bleep].
IT'’S EITHER FOR SHOW,
OR PEOPLE REALLY LIKE
TO [bleep] SPRINKLES.
- "PLEASE DO NOT TOUCH, LICK,
STROKE, OR MOUNT THE EXHIBITS."
- REALLY?
- IT'’S BEEN A PROBLEM
IN THE PAST.
- REALLY?
- PERVERTS.
- I'’M [bleep] FREAKED OUT,
AND I AM LIKE, "WHAT THE [bleep]
DID WE GET OURSELVES INTO?"
I FEEL LIKE A VIRGIN
IN THIS PLACE.
- SO HOW MUCH DO YOU GUYS
KNOW ABOUT ANIMAL SEX?
- NO.
- NO? NOT AT ALL?
- I NEVER HAD SEX
WITH AN ANIMAL.
- WELL, I WOULD HOPE NOT.
- ISN'’T THAT ILLEGAL?
- I DIDN'’T EVEN KNOW
THEY WOULD HAVE
AN ANIMAL SEX EXHIBIT
AT THE SEX MUSEUM.
- THOSE ARE BONOBOS.
THOSE ARE ACTUALLY TWO FEMALES.
- SO, MONKEYS HAVE,
LIKE, LESBIAN SEX?
- THEY DO.
- ROGER CALLS ME "MONKEY."
IT'’S GONNA TAKE A WHILE FOR
ROGER TO CALL ME MONKEY AGAIN
BEFORE I STOP
VISUALIZING TWO [bleep]
RUBBING AGAINST EACH OTHER.
WHAT'’S WITH THE THREESOME?
- OH, DEERS HAVE THREESOMES?
- MM-HMM.
- NO WAY.
- BUT THAT'’S
ANOTHER MAN ON A MAN.
- MM-HMM.
- SO, DEER CAN BE GAY.
- IT'’S VERY COMMON FOR DEERS
TO HAVE THREESOMES.
- OH, SEE, YEAH,
THE LITTLE ROCKETS. LOOK.
ME AND JENNI LEARNED
THAT MOTHER NATURE
IS ACTUALLY FREAKY.
- LET'’S PAY FOR OUR DILDOS
AND GO TO DINNER.
- [laughs]
- TABLE FOR TWO.
- FOR TWO? ALL RIGHTY.
IT'’S BASED ON A 16th CENTURY
JAPANESE CASTLE.
- IT'’S A WHAT?
- OOH, JAPANESE.
- JAPANESE, YEAH.
SO KEEP YOUR
EYES PEELED FOR NINJAS.
GOOD LUCK.
- OH, [bleep].
- THEY'’RE GONNA ATTACK US?
SO, WE WALK INTO NINJA, AND
RIGHT AWAY, THE HOSTESS IS LIKE,
"BE CAREFUL,"
AND I'’M LIKE,
"BITCH, I'’M PREGNANT.
IF SOMEONE [bleep] HITS ME,
I'’M GONNA KILL SOMEONE."
LIKE, THEY'’RE GONNA
COME OUTTA THE WALLS.
JENNI, I DON'’T LIKE THAT.
IS THIS A HAUNTED HOUSE?
- SHH. SHH.
- AAH!
girls: [scream]
- OH, MY GOD!
- JESUS!
- I JUST [bleep]!
I JUST PEED!
- COME ON IN, LADIES. WELCOME.
- I'’M NOT KIDDING, I JUST PEED.
[giggling]
I BEEN HOLDING IN MY PEE
FOR 20 MINUTES.
THANK YOU,
I JUST PEED MY PANTS.
- OH, MY GOD.
- I HAVE TO GO TO THE BATHROOM.
- COME ON, LADIES, ALL RIGHT.
- I'’M SO SCARED.
- I DIDN'’T KNOW THIS WAS
A [bleep] HAUNTED HOUSE.
JENNI?
- AAH!
- [screams]
- JESUS [bleep]!
WHY DO YOU DO THAT?
[laughter]
- LURKING IN THE SHADOWS,
LADIES.
YOU'’RE ONE STEP CLOSER.
COME ON, FOLLOW ME.
- [laughing hysterically]
- STOP.
WE LITERALLY
ARE TINKLING DOWN OUR LEGS,
BECAUSE WE GOT
SCARED [bleep]-LESS.
- BY A NINJA.
OH, MY GOD. YOUR FACE
WAS PRICELESS, BY THE WAY.
- WHAT'’D I DO?
[laughs]
THAT PLACE CREEPED ME OUT.
I-I WAS TURNED OFF
WHEN I LEFT.
YOU WEREN'’T?
- NOT REALLY.
IF THE ANIMALS WEREN'’T THERE,
IT WOULD'’VE BEEN A GREAT MUSEUM.
AFTER SEEING THE SEX MUSEUM,
I LIKE MY SEX
THE WAY I LIKE IT.
- ME TOO.
- I THINK IF THE BOYS
CAME TO THE SEX MUSEUM,
ME AND JIONNI WOULD BE
HAVING SEX IN THE BATHROOM.
- YOU'’RE A PIG.
- THAT'’S NOT FUNNY.
- [snorts]
- THAT WAS MEAN.
I FEEL LIKE JENNI
JUST CALLED ME FAT.
CRUEL.
- SORRY, I PICTURED
AN ANIMAL WHEN YOU SAID THAT.
- WHY?
- '’CAUSE WE JUST SAW
ANIMALS HAVING SEX.
I THINK NICOLE,
BEING PREGNANT,
IS TRYING TO ADJUST
TO HER SIZE.
I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD'’VE THOUGHT
ABOUT CALLING HER A PIG,
AND MAYBE WENT WITH
A DEER OR A DUCK.
ONLY YOU WOULD
BE ABLE TO HAVE SEX
AFTER YOU SAW
PIGS AND ANIMALS HAVE SEX.
- I'’M DONE.
GET THIS FOOD AWAY FROM ME.
- ARGH!
- [screams]
SERIOUSLY!
- PSYCHO!
ME AND NICOLE ARE
VERY PARANOID AT THIS POINT.
SO, WE'’RE WATCHING EVERY CORNER,
EVERY CREVICE--
WE'’RE LITERALLY TRYING TO RUN
OUT OF NINJA AS FAST AS WE CAN.
- THANK YOU.
- YOU'’RE WELCOME.
- ARGH!
girls: [scream]
I HATE YOU!
- [laughs]
- WAKEY-WAKEY, PREGNANT ONE.
- I'’M SO TIRED.
- YOU GOTTA GET UP.
IT'’S LIKE NOON.
SO, IT'’S A BEAUTIFUL DAY OUT
IN JERSEY CITY.
IT'’S NICE AND WARM,
AND WE HAVE A LOT OF SHOPPING
TO DO FOR THE HOUSE.
- HEY, LADIES,
WHAT'’S GOING ON?
- HI.
- ARE YOU PREGNANT?
- I'’M DUE NEXT WEEK.
- WHOO. GOOD LUCK.
- WHAT ARE YOU HAVING?
DO YOU KNOW?
- I DON'’T KNOW,
I LIKE THE SURPRISE.
- REALLY? DOES IT HURT?
- LOOK AT YOU.
- IT'’S GONNA HURT LIKE HELL
WHEN YOU PUSH THAT KID OUT.
- DID YOU GET THE EPIDURAL?
- HELL, YEAH.
- [laughs]
- AND DID IT HURT?
DID IT HURT AT ALL?
I RUN INTO THIS
PREGNANT LADY NAMED MEGAN,
AND SHE'’S AWESOME,
SO I'’M JUST, LIKE,
ASKING QUESTIONS, BECAUSE I
HAVEN'’T REALLY TALKED TO ANYONE
THAT HAS BEEN PREGNANT.
LIKE, I DON'’T KNOW
WHAT TO EXPECT,
OR WHAT'’S GOING ON.
DOES YOUR VAGINA
RIP TO YOUR BUTTHOLE?
- YEAH, I MEAN, IT CAN.
- UGH!
- DID YOURS?
- YOU NEED A GOOD DOCTOR.
YOU NEED A GOOD DOCTOR.
- I HAVE A GOOD DOCTOR.
- I HAD ONE STITCH.
- WELL, I DEFINITELY KNEW
THAT YOUR VAGINA
RIPS TO YOUR BUTTHOLE,
SO THE FACT
THAT SHE DID CONFIRM...
UGH.
THAT REALLY SCARES ME.
DOES IT FEEL LIKE
WHEN YOU HOLD FARTS IN?
- OH, NO, IT'’S SO MUCH
WORSE THAN THAT.
- [laughs]
- OH, I READ IN A BOOK
IT FEELS LIKE THAT.
- THE THING ABOUT IT IS--
IT'’S LIKE, ONCE YOU DO IT,
YOU'’RE LIKE,
"[bleep] HIGH FIVE!"
LIKE, YOU CAN'’T--
[laughter]
- LIKE, YOU JUST
FEEL LIKE YOU JUST DID
THE MOST AMAZING THING
ON THE PLANET,
AND LIKE,
NOBODY CAN MESS WITH YOU.
- THIS LADY
BASICALLY BROKE DOWN
WHAT PREGNANCY IS ABOUT
TO NICOLE,
AND I'’M KIND OF GLAD
NICOLE MET THIS LADY
SO SHE CAN HAVE SOMEONE
TO TALK TO HER
AND BE STRAIGHT-UP
WITH HER.
I'’M SO GLAD WE CAME BACK.
- BYE. GOOD LUCK.
- BYE, GUYS.
SEE YOU LATER.
- I WANNA BE LIKE HER
AT [bleep] NINE MONTHS,
READY TO POP.
- SO WHAT'’S
TODAY'’S CHECKUP LIKE?
- TO TEST IF IT'’S--
HAS DOWN'’S SYNDROME.
- THAT'’S TODAY?
- YEAH.
- SO, TONIGHT I HAVE
MY DOCTOR'’S APPOINTMENT,
AND I'’M VERY, VERY NERVOUS.
I FEEL LIKE ALL DAY
I'’M ON EDGE,
AND ALL I'’M THINKING ABOUT IS,
"OH, MY GOD,
WHAT IF MY BABY
ISN'’T HEALTHY?"
- DO YOU LIKE
YOUR DOCTOR, THOUGH?
- YEAH.
HE DELIVERED JIONNI.
- OH, REALLY? YOU'’RE GOING
TO JIONNI'’S MOM'’S DOCTOR?
- MM-HMM.
JIONNI'’S MOM, SISTER, AUNT...
- REALLY?
- IT'’S WEIRD, THOUGH, '’CAUSE
HE LOOKED AT ALL OF OUR VAGINAS.
- THE DOCTOR IS AN OB/GYN.
I DON'’T KNOW
WHAT THAT STANDS FOR,
BUT ALL I KNOW
IS IT DELIVERS BABIES.
- YOU READY TO GO
GET YOUR BELLY LOOKED AT?
- UGH, GOD...
- LET'’S DO THIS.
- MY BIGGEST FEAR
ABOUT TONIGHT'’S APPOINTMENT
IS THAT, YOU KNOW,
MY BABY IS NOT GROWING RIGHT,
AND IT'’S, LIKE,
NOT GONNA LIVE.
I MEAN, IT'’S VERY,
VERY STRESSFUL.
- I'’M EXCITED TO SEE
WHAT THE BABY LOOKS LIKE.
- IT'’S A LONG WAYS
TO GO, HONEY.
- I'’M REALLY NERVOUS
FOR NICOLE RIGHT NOW,
BUT I DON'’T WANNA SHOW IT.
I WANNA BE SUPPORTIVE,
AND I WANNA KIND OF, LIKE,
SNAP NICOLE
OUT OF BEING NERVOUS.
KIND OF LIKE WHAT ROGER
OR SOMEONE WOULD DO FOR ME
WHEN I START, LIKE,
MAKING MY HEAD SPIN.
- LIKE, AFTER THIS ONE,
I'’LL BE FINE,
'’CAUSE I KNOW
EVERYTHING'’S OKAY,
BUT THIS IS THE TEST
TO MAKE SURE IT IS OKAY.
- I'’M EXCITED FOR YOU.
- I'’M REALLY NERVOUS.
- THERE'’S MORE
SNOOKI &amp; JWOWWON THE WAY,
AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
- HERE WE GO.
- I HAVE TO PEE
REALLY BAD, HONEY.
- HI.
- HEY.
- LONG TIME.
- NERVOUS?
- YEAH.
WALKING INTO
THIS DR.'’S APPOINTMENT,
IT MEANS SO MUCH THAT
I HAVE MY BEST FRIEND HERE,
AND JIONNI, WHO IS
SO EXCITED TO BE A DAD.
IT'’S AWESOME.
IT'’S JUST A GREAT FEELING
TO HAVE LOVE, LIKE, EVERYWHERE.
- HEY, GUYS. HOW YOU DOING?
- HI. HOW ARE YOU?
- HOW YOU DOIN'’?
HEY, JIONNI, HOW ARE YOU?
- I'’M PAULA.
I'’M THE ULTRASOUND TECH.
- HI.
- HOW YOU BEEN?
- ALL RIGHT.
- HAVE A SEAT.
- OH, MY GOD.
- HOPEFULLY,
THE, UH, BABY BEHAVES.
AND SHE'’LL GET THE PICTURES
THAT SHE NEEDS.
- WE'’LL GET THIS DONE.
- SO HOW YOU BEEN FEELIN'’?
- EXHAUSTED.
- YEAH?
- REALLY FRICKIN'’ BITCHY.
- [laughs]
- SO CRANKY. MISERABLE.
- IS THAT TRUE?
- YEAH.
- AM I INTERRUPTING?
- HI. COME ON IN.
- LET'’S GO.
- COME ON IN.
- I'’M SWEATING,
I'’M SO NERVOUS.
IS THIS YOUR FAMILY DOCTOR?
- YES.
HI. I HEARD ALL ABOUT YOU.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
HOW YOU DOIN'’?
- JENNI.
- YOU SAW ALL THE VAGINAS
IN HIS FAMILY, I HEARD.
- OH, BOY. OH, BOY.
- THAT'’S NOT A BAD THING.
- YOU WANT THIS BACK?
- YEAH, PLEASE.
- OKAY.
- I'’M SWEATING RIGHT NOW,
I'’M SO NERVOUS.
- JENNI'’S THE GODMOTHER.
- THE GOD--
- DON'’T MAKE ME CRY.
IS THAT IT?
- YES, IT IS.
KID'’S STANDING ON HIS HEAD.
[laughs]
- STANDING ON ITS HEAD?
- WORST POSITION TO--[laughs]
- THAT HIS HEAD?
- THE LITTLE ARMS, LITTLE LEGS.
- SEE THE BABY MOVING AROUND?
- EWW!
- OH, IT'’S SO CUTE.
- THERE'’S THE LITTLE LEGS.
THERE'’S THE HEAD.
- IT'’S MOVING?
- IT'’S MOVING.
- YUP.
- OH, I GOTTA THROW UP.
[laughter]
- HOW AM I ABOUT TO CRY,
AND YOU'’RE, LIKE,
GONNA THROW UP?
- I WAS LIKE, "EWW!"
'’CAUSE IT--
IT LOOKED LIKE AN ALIEN.
- WHEN SHE SCREAMED "EW,"
I ALMOST--
- [giggles]
- I-I CHOKED BACK THE TEARS,
'’CAUSE I'’M LIKE, "GREAT,
THE MOM'’S NOT EVEN CRYING."
IT WAS JUST DOING
BACK FLIPS FOR YOU.
- CAN YOU TELL
IF IT'’S A BOY OR GIRL YET?
- NO, IT'’S A LITTLE SOON.
UH, LIKE, 20 WEEKS.
- SEEING MY CHILD
FOR THE FIRST TIME,
LIKE, ACTUALLY ON THIS SCREEN,
LIKE, THIS IS REAL.
LIKE, LIKE,
IT TOOK MY BREATH AWAY.
IT WAS A REAL
EXCITING MOMENT FOR US.
- THIS IS THE BABY'’S HEAD.
THIS IS LIKE A PROFILE.
- YOU CAN SEE THE NOSE, AND...
- THIS IS THE LITTLE NOSE,
AND NASAL BONES...
- COOL.
- YOU CREATED THAT.
DRUNK NIGHT.
- NO!
[baby'’s heartbeat]
- THAT'’S THE HEARTBEAT.
- HOW'’S IT SOUND? GOOD?
- VERY GOOD.
- NORMAL?
- MM-HMM.
- OH, YES.
- YOUR LITTLE BABY.
- IT HAS YOUR BIG NOSE.
- [laughs]
- I HAVE A BIG NOSE?
SHE GOES,
"AH, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEANT.
YOUR CUTE, LITTLE NOSE."
NOT WHAT YOU SAID.
YOU SAID I HAVE A BIG NOSE.
IT'’S OKAY.
I DON'’T HAVE A BIG NOSE.
I DON'’T KNOW WHY
SHE EVEN SAID THAT.
- EXACTLY.
- IT'’S JUST SO CRAZY TO ME.
- DOC, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
EVERYTHING'’S ALL RIGHT SO FAR?
- LOOKS GOOD, YEAH.
- YEAH.
- DR. RUSSO SAID
THAT THE BABY'’S AWESOME.
THE BABY LOOKS FINE,
EVERYTHING LOOKS PROPORTIONAL.
AND YOU KNOW,
THAT WAS A RELIEF TO HEAR,
BECAUSE I WAS SO WORRIED
OVER NOTHING,
BUT I GUESS THAT'’S
WHAT MOTHERHOOD IS.
ALWAYS WORRYING
ABOUT YOUR KID.
- PRAYING FOR A LOT OF THINS.
- I LOVE HIM ALREADY.
OH, MY GOD,
I LOVE HIM. OR HER.
- LOOK AT THE LEG.
- I KNOW, ISN'’T IT AMAZING,
JUST THE DEFINITION?
THE LITTLE LEGS. THE LITTLE LEGS
HERE, THAT LITTLE FOOT.
- I AM FEELING
SO MANY HAPPY EMOTIONS,
TO THE POINT WHERE
I JUST WANNA START CRYING,
BECAUSE THIS IS
MY LITTLE GODBABY.
LIKE, YOU KNOW, THIS IS
GONNA BE MY NIECE OR NEPHEW.
- YOU WANT TO TAKE THESE,
OR YOU WANT ME TO TAKE '’EM?
WANNA TAKE ONE OR TWO?
- NO, LET ME TAKE--
THE DOCTOR'’S APPOINTMENT,
OVERALL, I GIVE AN "A" PLUS,
BECAUSE EVERYTHING WENT WELL,
I HAD TWO PEOPLE THAT I LOVE,
BABY WAS HEALTHY,
AND IT WAS REALLY COOL
TO SEE IT FLIP AROUND
AND STUFF LIKE THAT.
SO, I'’M REALLY HAPPY WITH HOW
THE DOCTOR'’S APPOINTMENT WENT.
- HAVE ALL OF THESE
PAPERS HERE.
- THIS LITTLE,
FAT MEATBALL.
- LOOKS LIKE A SHRIMP.
- TAKES--TAKES AFTER US.
- [giggles]
- I THINK WE SHOULD
INVITE THE ROOMMATES OVER.
- HI.
- THIS IS AMAZING.
WHO WOULD EVER THOUGHT
WE'’D BE AT SNOOKI
AND JENNI'’S HOUSE FOR DINNER?
- THE REAL REASON
WHY I INVITED YOU GUYS HERE...
- UH-OH.
- IS BECAUSE
ME AND JIONNI ARE ENGAGED.
- WHAT?
- WOW!
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- I'’M A LITTLE UPSET
ABOUT THIS.