I'm resigning,
so it's kiss-my-ass time.
This is still my campaign.
Mr. Mayor,
the dick is up your ass,
and I am the one
who decides when it comes out.
Pezuela's verbal beat-down
was for this guy's benefit.
I'm guessing your intel about
a cartel evaluator was dead-on.
A guillermo beltran...
no wonder Pezuela
was trying to impress him.
His boss is in town.
You heard Vic turned in
his badge yesterday?
That leaves me to be
your most important instrument
in the gurrero cartel
investigation.
If you're no longer valuable
to Pezuela,
we're not sure you're valuable
to this investigation.
I'm looking for a place
to hide $100,000
where Vic won't find it.
Why does Vendrell
want you dead?
Vic thinks that Shane was
waiting at his place last night.
Shane Vendrell hired you
to kill Gardocki?
Mackey!
What happened to Shane?
He just left!
Every law-enforcement agency
statewide has a description
of Vendrell's vehicles
and recent pictures
of the family.
Shane and I
are getting out of town.
I am gonna call from wherever
we are and check in.
Vic and Ronnie are gonna do
everything in their power
to prevent the cops
from finding us.
We got to find them
before anyone else does.
That man over there
has a gun!
Vic tried to kill us
tonight, and you helped him.
When I call you tomorrow,
you need to have information
on how and where the police
are looking for us.
What did she say?
That they're not going to be
calling back here ever.
Who the hell are you?
Tell stella
we're here to see her.
Oh, she's asleep,
being the middle
of the goddamn night and all.
We're old friends
of her daughter's.
Well, I haven't seen Mara.
Since you boys drove
all the way from Los Angeles,
can I get you a drink?
The local police have
already been through here.
Stella told them
everything.
Why don't you pour yourself
a turpentine martini
and give us some air?
The last time I saw you,
my daughter got herself
in some trouble,
and you weren't
real nice about it, Vic.
Yeah, well, Mara's got herself
in an even worse jam.
You have any idea where
she and Shane might be headed?
Keeping your mouth shut
means you're aiding a fugitive.
You made that sound
so official.
It just doesn't seem legit,
though,
this whole midnight drop-by.
And I don't know shit
about where Mara's gone to.
Shane's dangerous.
It's not safe for Mara out there
or for Jackson.
And her pregnancy
could be in jeopardy.
Pregnancy?
Oh, well, this is a real fun way
to get the happy news.
Stella, how long has it been since
Mara's been in touch with you?
I stopped keeping track.
She used to help me out
with money,
and when she got married,
that all changed.
But if you find her,
you tell her I'm happy for her
with that baby.
Yeah, I'll be real sure
to do that.
Uh, give me a red bull.
Nice crowd for after-hours,
santi.
Tip well, and they leave
the lights on for you.
You're in the wrong side
of town, ain't you?
I'm here to give you
a reason to celebrate.
Name's Vendrell.
There's a reward waiting
for anyone who can deliver him.
Now, 10 grand... that'll buy you
an awful lot of cervezas.
You or any of your boys find
Vendrell, you hold him for me.
But be careful.
He's an ex-cop.
Call me at that number.
I show up with the money,
and we make the exchange.
This gonna get us into any shit
with your pals in blue?
It'll stay just between
you and me,
but I've already got
a few other search parties
after that cash,
so there will only be
one winning lottery ticket.
Keep it.
I'm not feeling very sentimental
these days.
Mara?
Hey, buddy.
Water warm?
Mmm.
It helps my back.
Want to come in?
Close your eyes.
It's like we're
off the coast somewhere...
...somewhere far, far away.
Soon, baby.
I promise.
Soon.
Nothing.
All right, Shane knows we were
already onto his last motel,
so he's probably looking for
a place to crash with less eyes.
My shift starts
in a couple hours.
All right.
You coming?
We're not gonna find him.
Sure we are.
We're betting our freedom
on gang leaders, Vic.
And that's
if any of them spot Shane.
I'm turning over every rock
I can.
I'm gonna run.
Hey, hey,
we're not there yet.
I call in sick to the Barn,
be across the border
before anybody knows about it.
It'll be a few days
before they even look for me.
Once you flip that switch,
there's no going back.
Iook, when they find Shane,
we're lifers in jail.
That's why we got to
find him first.
We had our chance.
Hey, man,
it's just like any other case.
Sometimes you just got to wait
until something hits.
I can't sit in the Barn
and wait.
If something goes down
and I don't hear about it,
all they got to do
is march across the bullpen
and slap the cuffs on me.
And how's your running
gonna make me look?
You should run, too, man.
Hey, hey...
this isn't something I haven't
thought of myself, okay?
Then, let's go.
No!
Let's go. No! Shane does not get to win.
He dropped the grenade
that killed our team,
but he doesn't get to kill
your career,
my life with my children.
This side gig I got going
with I.c. E...
It's going really well.
Now, I'm trying to insulate us
from all this shit,
set us up with jobs
and fed badges.
Why would they want to
bail us out, Vic?
Me helping out Olivia...
it's got her in my corner,
and she's whispering
in all the right ears.
All I got to do
is nail this shithead Mexican.
What, Pezuela?
Not Pezuela.
His boss, his cartel guy.
When that mousetrap springs,
I'll tell I.c.E. That it's time
for them to cut us a deal.
And you think
they'll go for that.
All I need is two,
three more days.
We keep looking for Shane,
or he stays hidden that long.
I turn it up a notch
with Olivia,
and then I toss your name in
when she starts talking terms.
Give me one last shot
at getting us through this shit.
If I fail, we'll both run.
* stay *
mom?
What's wrong?
Megan had a bad dream.
Didn't you hear her crying?
Uh, okay.
Um, go back to bed.
Come on.
You've got school
in the morning.
Come on.
It's ready.
Uh, nurse Mackey,
we're here about that
assault victim you called in.
Can you cover my beds for me?
Thanks, barb.
Before I say anything,
I need to be sure
that I can't get
into trouble for this.
Vic cannot know
that I came to you.
Anything you say
pertaining to this investigation
is protected.
You have my word.
No, I'm gonna need it
in writing.
I want my lawyer
to review it.
Corrine, it's us.
Just have the papers drawn up
and be back here in two hours.
What's the rush?
Is Vic planning something?
No, just be back here
in two hours.
Okay, Corrine,
we'll draw up
whatever documents you want,
but we're gonna need to know
what we're dealing with
right now.
Oh, God.
Shane and Mara contacted me.
They wanted information
about the police search.
Vic convinced me to go along
with it.
He lied to me, and he used me
to try to kill them.
I need Vic out of my life
for good,
but my kids cannot know
that I did this to him.
Arrest her and find out
what she knows in interrogation.
We arrest Corrine Mackey,
that leaves us limited
and dated information on Shane.
Now, we work with her,
that allows us to get to him.
She's admitted to having
regular contact with a fugitive.
She could be forced to cooperate
after being charged.
Corrine's only trying
to get free
from the web
that Vic has spun.
Now, she didn't have to
come forward.
We owe her.
Not to mention this could close
the book on Vic Mackey for good,
something that should
have been done a long time ago.
I gave Vic a pass
from time to time,
but only when he could
make a difference.
No.
You were sweeping him
under the rug.
He's made
a lot of good arrests.
I don't want
all those overturned.
The crimes Corrine
can help us get Vic on
are limited
to him and Shane.
It shouldn't jeopardize
any convictions.
Fine.
Let's give her
the help she needs.
How's early retirement?
Turns out it's not all hawaiian
shirts and fishing trips.
Yeah,
I heard about Vendrell.
Strike team's demise is even
more violent than I predicted.
End of an era,
but I'm already looking forward
to a new one.
Of course.
Vic Mackey doesn't hand over his
badge without an exit strategy.
I'm here to warn you
your golden parachute
might be about to rip.
Olivia gave me
a heads-up.
Guillermo beltran's
the new fed get.
Really?
Pezuela's an m.b.a.
With a dirty agenda.
This guy beltran...
he's the real power.
Which is why I.c.E. Needs me now
more than ever.
You think chaffee
and the lineup of budget
crunchers he answers to
gives a rat's ass about you,
about keeping you alive?
The moment beltran
crossed that border,
the rules of the game changed.
The feds want this guy so bad
they can taste it,
and they will not have a problem
shooting the messenger.
Oh, I see.
So you want me to just back off
and let you handle things
and gobble up all the glory.
Is that it?
There's only gonna be room
for one guy to work, beltran,
and that's gonna be me.
That's what I do.
Not anymore.
You're way in over your head,
councilman.
Working the Mexican cartel
from the inside out?
This isn't pushing paperwork
from the Barn to downtown.
This is real police work.
Pezuela's seen
your old photo album.
He doesn't fear you,
he doesn't respect you,
and beltran won't, either.
So do yourself
and your family a favor.
Step away from the table,
stay away from me,
and let the real men
finish this job.
Eat one of those hot dogs.
You know, baby...
yeah?
...it might be kind of nice
to find a place on the coast.
Mmm, I'd like that.
Hey, buddy, you ready?
Yeah.
Watch this.
Oh!
You see that?
You see what daddy's doing?
Yeah?
Bet you a hundred grand
could get us a place
even bigger than this.
You know what?
I bet you're right.
You gonna cook for me every day
down in Colombia, too?
No, I am going to hire us
a personal chef
to make us breakfast in bed
every single morning.
I love you.
All right,
daddy's gonna make his.
Mmm.
Okay, scoot over, buddy.
Come on.
Claro que sí, como no.
Did we have a meeting?
Think of this as roll call.
I'm clocked in
and ready for work.
If I need you,
I'll call you.
Well, I've had some extra time
on my hands lately,
thought I could keep busy
for the cause,
but, hell,
I get paid either way.
Haven't had the pleasure.
I'm Vic Mackey.
El es el policía anterior
sobre que te dije.
That's right.
I was a cop.
But now
I'm more of a favor granter.
What kind of favors?
I specialize
in the hard-to-deliver kind.
I guess you're a good guy
to know.
No, I'm not a real...
Vic Mackey.
Didn't expect to find you here.
So, are you
making new friends?
How do you know Cruz?
Just finishing some paperwork
on an old case.
What are you doing here,
David?
Well, you and I
need to talk...
in private.
Come back later.
Now, if you and I are gonna
continue in this arrangement,
then I need a course correction that
includes a restatement of my terms.
You don't get terms.
You get to be mayor.
Oh, I know.
But that'll be
with or without you.
I'm still deciding which.
Well, do you mind
giving us a hint
as to which way
you're leaning?
From now on...
you don't make any decisions
regarding my campaign,
who I work with,
or where I work out of.
¿entiendes?
I don't care how much you
or your investors contribute.
You are
my goddamned errand boy,
and you will do exactly
as you're told!
You're an empty suit.
You're a checkbook,
nothing more.
And just because
you hang out with tough guys
doesn't make you tough.
David.
Get back!
Get back, Vic.
You assaulted
a reserve police officer,
and that's a felony.
You have made
a very big mistake.
The only mistake I made
was letting you think
that I was your errand boy.
It's still
the other way around.
What the hell was that?!
I just proved my point.
You just blew
that I.c.E. Investigation
right out the window.
The one you're so desperate
to stay relevant to, huh?
By taking on the cartel,
you've opened yourself
to a world of possibilities,
all of them bad!
You're gonna
get yourself killed.
You know, beltran just saw
the same thing you just saw,
which means I'm gonna deal
with him directly from now on.
So, if you're
still fantasizing
about being I.c.E.'s connection
to the cartel,
well, you better get yourself
a new gig.
Here you go, captain.
Would you like me to stay?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
Mara came to see me
a few nights ago.
She claims that Vic and Ronnie
tried to kill Shane,
something having to do
with the armenians.
And Mara asked you
to help her and Shane
get police information
regarding them as fugitives?
Vic thought
it would be best
if Shane and Mara
left the country,
that it would be better
for all of us if they got away.
Instead, he tried
to track them down himself?
Did Ronnie have anything to do
with this hunt?
I don't know if Ronnie
helped him or not.
How did Vic find Shane?
He asked me about medication
that Jackson was taking.
Mara called me to say
that Vic had tracked them down
last night,
tried to kill them.
She's pregnant,
for God sakes.
I never liked her,
but she didn't deserve this.
Pay Vic a visit?
Not yet.
We've seen the hold
he's got on Corrine.
I'm not sure she'd be willing
to repeat that in a courtroom.
I'll use inglewood to set up
the tap on Corrine's phone.
That way, we won't trigger
any suspicion with Ronnie.
I'll park him with Billings
until we know
what his involvement is.
Steve will like that.
He's got a pretty big man crush.
I don't want inglewood
to know who this number's for.
You never know
how far Mackey's reach goes.
You think Vic's
got that many friends left?
Well, from here on out,
this investigation
is between us.
...9, 10!
Ready or not, here I come!
Where's Jackson?
Shh.
Nope, he's not in there!
Is he over here?
Nope!
I didn't know
you played the piano, baby.
Yeah, my mom made me
take lessons when I was a kid.
I was in class
with these four girls.
It didn't last long.
I was too busy
wanting to help my dad fix cars.
Wish I would have
kept at it, though.
Mm.
Where's Jackson?
Let's see.
There you are!
I found you!
Baby, look at him dance.
Come on, baby!
Show me your two-step,
little man.
Come on.
Come on, buddy.
Show me what you got.
All right, I'll tell him.
Should I come back?
What do you need, Steve?
I just got a call from
a detective in north Hollywood.
He asked if we'd interview a couple
locals for him on a murder case they got.
Oh, we're a little busy
right now.
Oh, it's just taking
a few statements,
eliminating them
as suspects.
I figure if Dutch and I
split up,
we can knock it out
by lunchtime.
Grab Gardocki.
Dutch is staying with me
on Vendrell today.
Oh, you catch a lead
on Shane?
What's going on?
We got nothing.
Hey, looks like you and me
are first string today.
What do you mean?
North Hollywood's got
a home-invasion murder.
So?
So, they want us
to do the interviews.
This is a chance for you and me
to chat things up.
You can tell me
how you met that asian hottie.
I want to stick around here and
see what breaks on the Shane thing.
Oh, sorry,
Claudette's orders.
Besides,
by the time we're done,
you could be speaking
to Vendrell in person.
What did you hear?
Dutch and Claudette are upstairs
playing "I got a secret,"
but it's real enough.
Vic and Shane
always seemed so tight.
Friendships do get tested,
I guess.
What's he doing here?
Mara?
Corrine, Vic's walking
up to your front door right now.
What do I do?
You on a landline
or a cordless?
Cordless.
Good. Just set the phone down,
act like it's off,
I'll keep the line open.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
It's almost 1:00.
I know it's a long shot,
but I thought maybe Shane
and Mara would call back.
She said she didn't trust us.
Remember?
She doesn't trust me.
Either way,
they're desperate.
Can I just come in
and wait around for a while?
You never know.
Hey, the place looks nice.
Yeah, I, uh, took advantage
of having the day off,
and I did some cleaning.
Iook, I know you never asked
to be a part of this.
I want you to know
I really appreciate you
pulling through for me here.
Just hang in there.
We're gonna miss the call.
Well, looks like
they kept their promise.
If you hear from them,
let me know right away,
okay?
I will.
Are you still there?
Yeah, he's on his way
to his car.
Hang up the phone.
Hello?
Why was the line busy,
Corrine?
I have two autistic kids,
Mara.
One of them knocked
the bedroom phone off the hook.
I'm sorry.
Tell me what you know.
They've expanded their search
to include other precincts.
All major throughways out of
the city are being watched.
What else?
They're going to release your
pictures for the evening news.
I'll call you back at 10:00.
Sounds like she's in.
I got nothing yet.
Iook at you,
beverly hills cop.
Been a long time.
What are Dutch
and Claudette up to?
They've been out all day.
I've been stuck in interrogation
with Billings.
Something's going on,
but I don't see
how I can find out what.
What about Billings? Can he
get something out of Dutch?
I'll try.
He wants to be
my best friend.
Ask Julien, too.
I'm not sure
what side he's on here.
It's better than nothing.
How's it going
with our I.c.E. Angle?
That's all looking good.
Hey, don't treat me
like Claudette.
What's the real deal here?
Right now,
it's all about Aceveda.
So, I got to get I.c.E.
To move away from him first.
Well,
how are you gonna do that?
With a little help
from you.
You got a drink
you can recommend here?
How did you know
I was here?
More mysterious
if I don't tell you.
This conversation
will be a lot longer if you do.
Waited outside of Pezuela's
place for you to come out,
see which car
you were driving.
We got the plate,
and I had a friend of mine
in the department
put your car on a watch
and advise.
10 minutes later,
we got a hit
your benz was sleeping
outside in this parking lot,
and here I am.
You still got juice
with the police, huh?
Enough to make a screwdriver
for every vato in I.a.
I don't know who you are,
exactly,
but judging by the way
Pezuela puffed up his chest
when I first got there,
I'd say important...
which means you're cartel.
Pretty high up, too.
Can I guess
why you're here?
Pezuela's screwing up...
body draggings,
public assassination,
pointing the finger
at your organization
while he walks around
in a suit and tie,
more interested
in his big buildings
than doing business
for you.
Getting his ass kicked
by a politician today...
that couldn't have inspired
much confidence.
We don't work well
with outsiders.
Who do you think...
He's not gonna be looking
for a dead man.
has been cleaning up
Pezuela's mess?
You want to prove yourself
to me?
Try me.
I never want to
see his face again.
Pezuela?
Show me the cop
washes off of you.
Hey, hey, someone's here.
Shit.
Um, finish getting him dressed.
They're not coming by
for another hour.
I wanted to get here early
and air the place out.
I thought I heard someone.
Hi, I'm debbie paluf.
I'm with keller.
You scared me. Why didn't you
leave the door open?
Oh, I have a single dad
in there.
He has a toddler, and he wanted
to make sure the locks worked.
He's a very nervous guy.
I'll call you back.
Bill said they weren't
showing this place till 4:00.
Oh, yeah, probably.
I was actually showing my guy
a place over on belden
and we drove by
and he saw the sign,
so I called hillary gratham,
and I asked her
for the lockbox code.
Can I ask you a question
about the schools around here?
Oh, hi.
Hi.
Mr. Wilson,
apparently this house
is being shown to another buyer
at 4:00 today.
Ah. Well, I better make my
decision quick then, huh?
I'm not sure
if debbie showed you already,
but did you see
the back patio's
been newly re-tiled
with terra-cotta and the...
what are you?
Oh, my God.
Take her cellphone.
Take her keys. Come on.
Don't hurt...
please don't hurt me.
Please don't.
I beg you.
My husband, my daughter...
just shut up already!
Just shut up!
Aah!
Hey,
how's the Shane thing coming?
Hard, like trying to find
a needle in 10 haystacks.
Dutch, so, you think
that Shane's still in I.a.
Like I said, Steve,
we got nothing.
A realtor was forcibly detained
by an armed man and woman
when she found them squatting
in one of her homes.
They locked her in a pantry
before escaping in her car...
Shane and Mara.
Where?
Los feliz.
Unis say she was locked up
for about an hour
before another realtor
arrived with clients.
I'll call their captain
and see can he quietly
get a few cars over there.
We should pull a few of ours,
as well, get them all in there.
Right, right, right.
Julien, you got a second?
Sure. What's up?
I need you to issue a message
on the m.d.t.
This about Vendrell?
Yeah, and I don't want it
to go out on the radio.
Beltran gave me
my first task today.
Apparently, he's not happy
with your job performance.
He sent me to kill you.
Lucky for you,
we don't play on the same team.
I work for Olivia Murray.
That's right.
Agent Murray
has a few questions for you,
asked if I could
bring you in.
I'm gonna need you
to give me back her file
before we head over there.
That file's all I got
on that bitch.
That bitch will send you
out on the street
at the cartel's mercy
if I tell her to.
You're about to get something
that nobody ever gets...
a second chance.
For a guy who could be facedown
in the I.a. River,
you don't seem
very cooperative.
You were green-lit, Cruz.
You understand how lucky you are
that beltran gave the hit
to a guy who was
working undercover for us?
If beltran wants me dead,
I'm dead.
If I talk, it just gives him
more incentive to find me.
How are you gonna protect me
from that?
We'll give you
a new life.
What's that?
A townhouse in phoenix?
No, thanks.
Why don't you give
your boss a ring,
tell him it looks like
we're gonna be here for a while?
Well done.
You keep stonewalling like this
for the next couple of days,
I promise you I will deliver
beltran to them myself.
You walk out of this
without a scratch.
Beltran will never stop
looking for me.
It's gonna be a slow go,
but Pezuela will talk
eventually.
How long before he starts
talking about my file?
Don't worry.
I'm headed over to his place
right now to get the box.
We have to convince beltran
that I took out Pezuela.
That way
I'll have earned my keep.
Me becoming the new Pezuela...
your bosses aren't gonna
get any closer than that.
They're content to use David.
Sure, maybe David can clue you
in on beltran's master plan.
What plan?
Well, from the little beltran
clued me in on this afternoon
when I spoke to him,
it sounds like he's starting up
a money-laundering scheme
that would make
ivan boesky flinch.
But you can get the details
from your boy Aceveda.
Okay.
Let me make
another phone call.
What's that?
This is a police scanner.
That way, we can at least have
some ears on their movement.
Baby, I think
we should get out of California.
No, not yet.
It's gonna take
a lot of manpower
to check
all those empty homes.
It should keep them busy
until the motorcade hits town.
So, all we've got to do
is make it through tomorrow,
and we'll be in the clear.
And I know a place where
we can stay in the meantime.
I'm guessing it probably
doesn't have a pool.
You know,
there was a minute today
when you were playing piano
and Jackson was dancing,
I actually...
I actually forgot about
everything that was going on,
and I was just...
I was just happy.
Every day's gonna be
like that in Colombia, babe.
Yeah.
I promise, okay?
Now, what's going on
with the little man?
He's hungry.
Well, I'm pretty sure
I can fix that.
I have some sad news
for you.
A colleague of yours
committed suicide tonight,
blew his brains out
in his office.
You'll be reading about it
in tomorrow's paper.
And how do the policia
know it's a suicide?
Because the gun in his hand
is gonna match the bullet
they find in his brain.
An assortment of alcohol
and drugs will seal the deal.
It means there won't be
any investigation.
Now, if I'm not mistaken,
that means there will be a hole
in your organization.
Where do I submit
an application?
Sorry, buddy.
La placa.
Aquí busca sandy.
That's that punk right there.
That's him.
Hold up there, homes.
Whoa, hey, whoa.
Fellas, I'm a cop.
Not no more.
Grab his heat, dawg.
Shane, what's going on?
It's okay, baby.
I got it.
Hey, hey, man, hey.
Ho, ho, ho, ho.
Bitch, get out the car.
Man, she's got my kid in there,
all right?
No, no, no, no, no.
Hey, call santi.
Tell him we got his guy.
Hey, homey, you must have really
pissed off your cop buddy.
He's paying 10 g's
for your head, esé.
Hey, look, man,
before you make that call,
maybe we can do
some business ourselves.
Unless you got 10 grand,
the only business we got
is selling your ass.
Well, today's your lucky day,
'cause I... I got 20.
That's the easiest cash
you boys will ever make.
It's 10 grand apiece. All
you got to do is keep walking.
You carry
that kind of green?
If I do,
does that mean we got a deal?
You walk away.
You leave my wife and my kid.
You leave us alone.
Sure, let's see it.
Mara, get the money.
Go ahead, baby.
That's all you got
in the bag.
Come on, man.
I thought we were straight.
Oh, shit.
Homey,
there's more than 10 g's...
come on, man!
We had a goddamn...
that's before you were rich,
white boy.
All right, fine.
Fine, you got almost 100 grand
in there.
That's more than enough
to keep walking.
Why walk away with 100
when I could walk away with 110?
A cop is looking for me.
First thing he does when
he gets here is flash a badge,
and he takes that money.
Trust me.
Iook, you got two choices.
You can take the $98,000 and
change that you got right there,
or you make that call
and you see how much
you walk away with then.
Just wanted
to let you know
that Pezuela
killed himself tonight.
Really?
Didn't seem the type.
You know, I've been following
your career, councilman.
You're like a fish
swimming through razor blades.
I'm impressed.
I'm glad you approve.
Relájate, man, relax.
I'm not like Cruz.
I don't like to micromanage.
I like to stay focused
on the bigger picture.
Besides,
you're the politician here.
You can decide
how to run your campaign.
Hire who you want,
target the areas you want,
focus on the issues
you want.
Just don't lose.
I won't.
The fruit growers union
are going to be announcing
their formal support
for your campaign.
You know those campesinos.
They need a place
to keep their earnings.
And immigrants...
we don't...
we don't trust
American banks.
And I have a suggestion
which would be beneficial
to all of us.
But that's for later.
Well, great, I look forward
to their support and yours.
Hello.
They came after us again.
Who, Vic?
We have our 2-year-old son
with us.
We could have
all been killed.
What kind of animal
did you marry?
What happened, Mara?
What did Vic do?
He put a bounty on our heads
with the gangs.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
Mackey.
Hey, asshole.
Shane?
As punishment for the shit
you tried to pull today,
there is a letter
on its way to the Barn
addressed to Claudette Wyms,
a written confession of one
of your many sins from the past.
And which sin
would that be, Shane?
I'll let that be
a surprise,
but you and Ronnie had better
get used to being cell mates
for the next
three to five years,
assuming you can't bullshit
your way out of it.
Either way,
it'll keep you two off my ass
for the next few days
trying to intercept it.
This is our ax to grind, Shane.
You leave Ronnie out of it.
Come on, Vic.
We both know you're not shit
without your badge.
There's no way you could have
got that close to me
without your little Vic
back at the Barn.
Now for your contrition,
since you caused us
to lose all of our cash today,
you're gonna replace it...
$100,000.
And I want it
by 5:00 P.M. Tomorrow.
I'm gonna need
more than a day.
I don't give a shit
what you need.
I can't get it together
that fast. You know that.
This coming from the guy who
masterminded the money train?
Please.
You'll figure it out.
Shane's on the phone with Vic
right now,
giving him a task
to carry out.
Please make sure
that he does it.
I just want this
to be over with, Corrine.
Me too.
Now, Corrine is gonna handle
delivering the money to us.
I will call her tomorrow
with a location at 1:00 P.M.
Hey, hey, hey, Corrine's
done enough for you already.
You stop trying to shield
yourself behind my ex-wife.
You man up,
and you let me come and deliver
that cash to you myself.
What,
so you can get another shot
at my pregnant wife
and son?
No, thank you.
I didn't put Mara
in the crosshairs, Shane.
You did when you decided
to involve her in our shit.
Corrine delivers
the money tomorrow,
or my next love letter
to Claudette
is about the bullet that you put
under Terry Crowley's left eye.
Let's see how much the cops back
at the Barn adore you then.
What?
We got to figure out a way to
put 100 grand in Corrine's hands
by tomorrow afternoon.
I can't go
through this again, Corrine.
Just make sure Vic does
what we want him to do,
or I don't know
what we're gonna do.
Mara, this is Claudette Wyms.
Please don't acknowledge me yet.
I want to get you and Shane
out of this mess.
If you and Shane are willing
to talk about Vic Mackey,
I'm willing to listen.
Mara, I can hear
the desperation in your voice.
There is still time
to turn this around.
You've got two options.
Come in now,
and I'll grant you immunity.
I can't promise
the same for Shane,
but I can guarantee
that it will be a better deal
than Vic will get.
Or you can keep on running
until we catch up with you.
Then it'll be
a whole nother scenario.
You'll be giving birth
in a state penitentiary.
Your baby will be taken
from you... Jackson, too.
They'll be put in the system.
Do you want your children
to be in foster care, Mara?
Be a mother to your children
and do what's right for them.
I can't talk right now.
I want you to know
that all I want from this
is Vic Mackey behind bars.
That's it.
If you are interested
in helping me do that,
then you find a place
where you can talk,
and you call me tomorrow
morning, 8:00, this line.
Okay.
I think we got to her.
So, how did it go?
Corrine's working
with the police.
It's okay.
It'll be okay.
Transcript by www.1000fr.com