Pervioulsy on the shield
the armenians
know about the money train!
Diro green-lit your family.
If we just work together
on this thing...
We don't work together
on shit anymore.
You had me arrested.
You make the case go away.
As long as I'm locked up
in here, everything's at risk.
Shane is neck-deep
in Armenian shit.
We got to keep him close.
Vic's had this ex-cop
watching us all day long,
and I don't know what's going on
between...
I do. He didn't know about
the bogus Armenian threat.
Shane was acting out
on some bullshit tip
from some banger in county.
I guess one of us
is being lied to.
This is Cruz Pezuela.
This city
needs cops like you.
I have larger interests
I'd like to protect.
Found out the name
of one of your former employees
who was stealing secrets...
Luis aramboles.
Pezuela doesn't know
you lost their blackmail files.
No.
What about the files?
He sold them to rezian.
The armenians are making a hard
play for your barrio sandbox.
Looks like I'm gonna need you
to get my family clear of this thing.
Make rezian believe the Mexicans
are the armenians' worst problem.
This is L.A., baby.
It's latino land,
and I know every Mexican gang
from here to sinaloa,
which means that nothing happens
to Vic's family
or you lose the only guy who can
stop your Mexican threat.
I got the Mexicans thinking
that the armenians are making
a power play for the barrio.
So, what now?
We can just sit back,
watch the gang war.
www.1000fr.com presents
Sync: Vine
bring back memories?
On a clear night, you can
see Guardo's house from here.
Don't worry.
I haven't seen his ghost around.
Come on.
Who's the amigo?
Luis aramboles.
Intel operative
for the mexis.
He came up here
to start some shit.
I told your boss you sold his
box of sins to the armenians,
which means you're breathing
on borrowed time.
He won't believe that.
They're already out
looking for you.
Price on your head...
I could retire.
It's time to disappear...
Unless you want me
to just turn you over.
Who's he?
Someone who wants to help you
with your travel arrangements.
He would never want to see
an... innocent man get killed.
Hey.
Hey!
You want to give me a clue
what all this is about?
He's the key to defusing
the Armenian time bomb
you laid
at my family's doorstep.
He's the keeper of the intel
the mexis are using
to blackmail
their way to the top.
Or was,
till I helped myself.
And you made it look like this
prick sold out to the armos.
Which lit the fuse for
the blood feud we're stirring up
between rezian
and the Mexicans.
Nicely done.
Aramboles is the only one
who can put my face to the grab.
So he's got to go away.
I need you to hook him up
with the coyotes we were using
to get Lem set up
down in Mexico.
Who's he working for?
I want him gone
by tomorrow night.
Getting him out of the country's
not a problem.
Setting him up on a goat farm
with money and contacts,
it would be nice to know who
and what I'm dealing with.
Working with you to protect
my family...
I'm down with that.
Trusting you?
Not there yet.
S7E02
that's a mistake.
You should have
come to me first.
This piece of shit
rezian...
He's taken something
that belongs to me.
So drop a couple of low-level
Armenian bodies on the street.
Scare them into getting
your blackmail box back,
but trying to whack rezian now
goes too far too fast.
It's already in motion.
Be prepared
to help me control the blowback.
When's this going down?
Today.
We have some people
in county jail where he's at.
Look, when all hell breaks loose
out on the street because of this...
It's gonna
hurt your business.
And it's gonna hurt my ability
to protect you.
I'm confident you'll be able
to handle the job adequately.
Any other questions?
Not at the moment.
Hey, Tina,
have you seen shane?
No, haven't had
the pleasure today.
What the hell is this?
The mayor just released a list
of the top-10 most wanted gangs
to a press conference
this morning.
Hey, are we making celebrities
of these douche bags now?
It's the latest initiative
in the city's war on gangs.
It's just gonna get sets
competing to move up the ladder.
Gang crime's up 14%
citywide this year.
While Farmington's numbers
are down.
I guess
I can't be everywhere.
I weighed in against this
with Phillips.
I was told that the mayor
wants to be proactive
in identifying gang problems
to reassure the public.
Well, it made the front page,
so hang on.
Well, fortunately, most of these
bangers can't read.
Still, I got the over/under on one
of these crews doing the first whack
to move up the list
in three hours.
I'll take the under.
Rumor has it that you're
scheduled for a new hearing.
Four weeks from today.
Well, if you would like to spend
that time with your lawyer,
your pba rep organizing
your case...
As long as I got this,
I'm gonna use it.
Nice try, though.
Arrangements
have been made.
??? Have aramboles
ready at 10:00.
This war we started is already
spinning out of control.
Mexicans have overreacted.
Rezian's been green-lit.
They're gonna make a move
against him tonight.
Protecting rezian
is the only thing
that's keeping
your family alive.
I'm not the one behind this.
We need to get rezian
in protective custody.
It's too late for that.
He'll be dead
before the request is processed.
Jesus.
Okay.
Okay, maybe...
Maybe my Armenian problem
goes away.
With rezian dead,
maybe he's the only armo
who knows enough about me
to hold a grudge.
Or maybe Armenian number 2
knows what rezian knows
and blames us
for getting the boss whacked.
You have to warn him.
Yeah, so he can get himself
in the right frame of mind to take a shiv?
No, I'll figure out
how to head that off.
Meanwhile, you get cred
by giving him a heads-up,
and he'll owe you.
How you holding up?
Oatmeal and bologna.
I haven't had a woman
in weeks.
Well, oatmeal's good
for the colon.
You think this is funny?
The D.A.'s
squeezing the accountant
who did my books at the port.
He agreed to turn evidence.
He's being deposed
this afternoon.
I'll see what I can do.
Meantime, you got
a much bigger problem.
I got word
that you're hard candy.
You've been green-lit
by the Mexicans.
The Mexicans? Why?
Look, you just need
to watch yourself
until I can get you
moved into protective custody.
I am going to protect you.
You better.
You know why?
Anything happens to me,
I've already given the order to
go after your friend's family.
And yours, too.
If I wanted you dead,
I wouldn't warn you.
Then let's just call it
incentive.
I guess some of these bangers
can read.
This is John layton,
Pasadena address,
no priors, no witnesses,
at least none
of the sharing kind.
What's Mr. Layton from Pasadena
with no priors
doing walking around
this stretch of misery?
Gang turf,
upscale victim... drugs?
This is not
where whitey scores his powder.
Century Boulevard caters more
to the pale-face group.
He's got over $100 in cash
in his wallet.
It's no robbery.
Maybe trying to pick up a trick?
The stroll's
six blocks that way.
These tags...
Los mags, one niners...
This is gang central.
We all know what this is.
Only difference is, you're the
one who has to call the mayor
and tell him that his list
got a white guy popped.
We don't know
it's top-10 related.
Drive-by?
Look, this list is like the
standings in the sports section,
and every gang
is making a playoff push.
Find the shooter.
Okay, Vic and I
will take the one niners...
No, no, no, no.
Shane comes with me.
L-I'll bring him up to speed.
You and Julien
go press the Los mags.
How'd rezian
take the bad news?
He's a big believer
in life insurance.
He gets whacked, they come after
your family and mine.
We got to figure out how many
rungs on the Armenian ladder
know about
our money-train rip-off.
Jesus Christ!
How'd we lose control
of this?
Rezian's accountant's
about to give him up.
He expects me
to hose him down.
If we don't,
that screws us up, too.
The accountant... later.
Keeping rezian alive... now.
Moses.
Just crashing by
to say, "what up?"
Redecorating?
This is all your boys.
Pigs blew through here
like a damn hurricane.
Tossed
my breezie's crib, too.
Shut down my weed spot
around the way,
and I ain't done no harm.
You waking up in the morning
does harm.
Dead bodies on your turf...
Not a good look, Moses.
Like I told po-po,
don't know nothing about it.
Didn't stop them
from messing up my place.
I guess you don't know nothing
about the top-10 list in the paper, either.
I know we reppin' at number 5.
I'm good with that.
Blow a hole in a white man,
you get respect,
shot at number 1.
I'm a businessman.
And merking white folk
is a no-go for my commerce.
What about one of your baby
bangers trying to earn cred?
One of my g's wildin' out,
I'd have heard.
There's plenty of nigs out there
perpetrating felonious bullshit.
Why don't you swarm on them?
Stay out of my grill.
Who else would pull a Jack move
like this?
Athens, piru, spook street.
Spook street
didn't even make the list.
What I'm saying.
They need to step they game up
or they out.
You got any soldiers
in county, Moses?
Do I got soldiers in county?
We straight claiming county
as one nine turf.
Got a deal for you.
We have an associate
locked up there.
Needs protecting.
I ain't doing Jack for you
till this shooter's gaffled up.
Keep the cops out of my shit.
You do this, I'll make sure
our guys back off.
You got till 4:00 to make
the streets smooth
so I can be about my paper.
Then I'll see about your boy
in county.
Deal.
Please get these people
behind the yellow tape.
Victim's lana boyle.
Looks like a cinder block
fell and killed her.
Death from above.
This is Doug obermyer.
Victim's his girlfriend.
I'm detective Wagenbach.
This is detective Billings.
I'm really sorry.
Dude, one of those assholes
murdered her!
You think
this wasn't an accident?
Those goddamned beaners
have been hassling us
ever since
we rented this space.
Um, this is a commercial
building?
It's a rehearsal space.
Lana was our lead singer.
Yeah, rent's cheap
in this neighborhood.
The tenants next door
didn't like the music?
It was one of them, man.
They killed her.
You're gonna
arrest somebody, right?
We're gonna talk to people,
try and determine what happened.
I was out here
when it happened!
They was yelling out of the
window, bitching at us to move!
And... and you didn't?
If they don't like our smoke,
they can go back to Mexico city
and choke on the smog!
Okay, Doug, Doug,
don't go away.
I may need
to talk to you again, okay?
I wonder if rock-Star bo???
Is more upset about losing
his girl or his lead singer.
Somebody did drop
that cinder block intentionally,
probably a resident.
Maybe still in the crowd.
Oh, right. I'll, uh, get a read.
Don't want to put you out.
I interviewed
the boys in the band.
They were all out here
when it happened,
but nobody was looking up
when the cinder block
came tumbling down.
The band was just here
taking a smoke break.
I need you to track down
the building manager.
I want every tenant
with a window view of the street
brought down here.
Policia.
We need everyone
outside now.
Policia!
Hey!
Come on out!
We can hear you in there!
Great. We respond to a murder.
We get a domestic.
Luna puta!
Iabre la puerta ahora!
- What?!
- HEy!
A little more respect!
And didn't you
hear us knocking?!
Listen up.
A girl was killed outside.
We need everyone
downstairs now.
Nothing to do with us.
Icierra la pinche puerta!
Step aside.
And you shut up.
Tell your woman
to put some clothes on
and get downstairs
for questioning right now.
Hey! Put your hands
where I can see them now!
He was getting a shirt to cover her up
like you asked him to.
Total news blackout on anything
gang-related until further notice.
Wouldn't have anything to do
with the businessman
being shot this morning?
Whatever the reason,
something like this happens,
it's a tragedy.
And the timing
couldn't be worse.
And because the mayor doesn't
want to fuel speculation
that his gangbanger hall of fame
is the cause.
- WHo's working the case?
- STrike team.
Mackey in the mix?
- FRont and center.
- GOod.
Oh, don't tell me you're
drinking his kool-aid now, too.
Am I the only one
who will remember
the trail
his tornado left behind
if and when he's finally
thrown out of here?
I'm under no illusions,
but a day like this one?
I can live with him.
Who's that guy?
Jamal
just replaced trinitron
as the number-one shot-caller
for spook street,
although he claims to be just another
downtrodden black man in the struggle.
Join the club.
You know what the street's
saying about your set?
Calling you the clown posse,
as in laughing at you,
not with you.
Hauling me out of bed without
letting me take my calm pills.
Spook street's a joke.
They in my pocket.
Forget to take them
yesterday, too.
And y'all are making me
on edge.
Hey, my wife... she takes these
when she's on the rag.
Maybe I should
get you a tampon, too.
You gave the order
to merk that white guy,
let people know that
spook street's still around.
Maybe you can get spook street
on that top-10 list.
Hell, they could put together
a top-100 list.
Your piece-of-shit crew
wouldn't be on it.
How am I trying to beef with
some white dude I never seen?
Maybe you were just trying to
lay down the law,
trying to get your soldiers
to come correct,
Pasadena square biz
walks into your line of fire...
Look,
if this was accidental,
maybe one of the guys in your
crew has an itchy finger,
we can help.
All you got to do
is tell us the truth.
Man, I got kids to feed...
Another one on the way.
My moms is dying.
I ain't a clown.
I ain't a bitch.
Just trying to look out
for my own, make my way.
A man of peace.
With the most high
as my witness,
I didn't shoot no man.
Don't know about no shooting.
Now, please,
can I have my pills?
Any gang presence
in the building...
Young men, tattoos,
baggy t-shirts?
Yeah, I know what gang members
look like.
Nah, it's mostly families.
They pay their rents on time,
and they keep to themselves.
Complaints about the noise
and the smoking next door...
Anybody
particularly more upset?
Nobody's complained to me,
and I can't think
of anybody here
who would do anything
like this.
Where were you
when it happened?
At the hardware store
to get a pipe fixture
for a broken toilet.
Um, thanks.
I'm gonna need that tenant list.
Sure.
Can I, uh...
Steal him for a minute?
I'll be back.
You get
any good information?
If you mean her phone number,
no, thanks to you.
If this is the Billings level
of effort I can look forward to,
you may as well just go home.
No, me interviewing a witness
is just as good as you doing the same.
I'm the only one working
at maximum capacity.
Really? What did you
come up with so far?
Hey, Dutch,
I talked to every tenant
with an apartment
on this side of the street,
and every single one of them
says they didn't see anything.
Same here.
Looks like they'd rather be
watching their novelas
than help I.D. A killer.
Yeah, don't worry.
Dutch is on the case.
Young woman
got her head bashed in.
You're not disturbed
by the apathy?
Why don't you
take a look around you?
We've been standing
in the hot sun for how long now,
and we are
right where we started.
So if you've got some magic beans
in your detective bag of tricks
that'll make these people
give a shit,
why don't you start
planting them?
You know what, Steve?
You're right.
We have been here a while.
Excuse me!
Could I have your attention?
I'm pleased to announce
that, today, you're all
gonna have the pleasure
of seeing your local tax dollars
at work up close and personal.
Since none of you
want to do the right thing here,
you're all coming down
to the Farmington station
for continued questioning.
And until someone comes forward
who saw what happened,
I'm gonna make all of your lives
as inconvenient
and unpleasant as possible.
Have a nice day.
Better get a bus down here.
What's up?
Colorado plates.
Visiting usc for graduation.
And they thought tuition
was a bitch.
Same neighborhood, m.o.,
victim profile.
Hey, Claudette...
You need to be back
at the office on spin control.
We got this.
You're not
used to a short leash?
I'm fine.
I saw what happened!
I was right over there,
and I saw it all.
You need
to stop snitchin', bitch!
Why you helping one time?!
You need to mind your mouth
and get back to your mama!
You a straight rat,
you old fool!
Stop snitchin'!
I lived in that building
for 40 years,
and I seen these young folks
turn these streets into living hell!
No snitchin'!
Why don't you let us
take you back to the station,
where you can make a statement
someplace quiet?
For safety?
I'm not scared.
I'm too old for scared.
My sons are in jail.
My lesbian daughter
won't give me grandchildren.
They want to kill me?
I can't wait
to see my Jesus.
Did you get a look
at the shooter?
There were two,
and they were in Gray do-rags.
Spook street.
You just told me
you ruled them out.
Jamal lied his ass off,
and I bought it.
Can you give us a physical
description of these men?
Age, height, tattoos?
They wasn't no men.
They were like 13 or 14...
Maybe.
They were babies...
Babies on bicycles.
Hey, Moses!
Yo!
The shooters are spook street.
Case closed.
Now, call up your boys
in county.
They need to be on the lookout
for this Armenian dude.
His name is rezian.
Byz lats is looking
to put him down.
Only you're not
gonna let that happen.
So get off the weed
and get on the phone
with your boys in county.
You have a window
that faces the street.
You didn't see
what happened?
I always
keep my blinds closed.
Even on a hot day
like today?
When I'm in my apartment,
I like to be naked.
Thanks.
Excuse me.
Where'd you get those?
From that man.
Oh, come on.
Hey, Asher, take this lying
piece of shit Jamal upstairs.
Hey, guys.
What a surprise.
Busy day.
What's going on?
Why do you have somebody
watching us and following us?
You didn't get a tip
from some banger in county.
Mara told me
about the whole Armenian thing
you and shane
are mixed up with.
- NOw, what's the truth?
- HEy, calm down.
Let's not do this here, okay?
Come on.
Cass, don't move.
What the hell is going on?
I'm handling it.
Oh, handling it is by tying up
Mara and gagging her?
That's a gross exaggeration.
Look, shane got
both of our families in a jam,
which I am currently
getting us all out of.
- I Need you...
- tRust you, right?
We were working
an undercover job.
Believe me, you don't want
to know the details.
Now,
Shane used bad judgment.
That's why you have some ex-cop
following me?
He's just there to...
He's just there to make sure
you're all right.
Look...
...the truth is,
something might be going down.
I want to move you guys
to a hotel.
I don't believe this.
I'm done.
I'm going to connecticut...
My cousin's.
I need you to stay in town
where me and my guys
can look out for you.
If you think I would let anyone
hurt you or my children,
you don't know me.
Do you work here?
Eight hours a day,
minus half-hour for lunch.
You need some change
for the vending machine?
I want someone arrested
for a crime.
Yeah?
Who's that, sweetheart?
My father.
Got a call claiming
responsibility for the murders.
We already know
it's spook street.
Caller confirms it's spook
street working with Al-qaeda.
Al-qaeda in the hood?
This is serious.
Knock yourself out.
But it's bullshit.
I've seen the FBI report.
There's internet chatter.
Terrorist groups are trying to
get in business with local street gangs.
We're rolling
on internet rumors now?
Hell, on the internet, Dutch boy
is still a 13-year-old girl
looking
for her first training bra.
Terrorists funding their operations
by selling drugs and weapons
to gang members
who deal drugs and weapons...
How is that a stretch?
Look, we spend all day,
every day, in the barrio.
That's just not
what's going on.
How does it look
if we do nothing
and, God forbid,
the unthinkable happens?
It's the world
we're living in now.
All right.
We'll work the international
terrorist angle.
We've already notified
homeland security.
They'll be taking over
from here.
When the men from u.n.c.I.E.
Are cruising alvarado
looking for osama,
I'll be sweating some good, old-fashioned,
trash-talking American dipshit.
Jamal...
Lying to me
is unacceptable.
Man, I told you the truth
and nothing but the truth.
Yeah, with the most high
as your witness. I know.
Only I got a witness, too,
saw the shooters
in spook street colors.
Then there's some niggas
out there false flaggin'.
Listen, shithead!
The feds are gonna be here
in a minute.
Once they get here,
I can't help you.
Oh, white people get shot,
and it's a federal case now?
Oh, we're way past
black and white.
Which means you got a rainbow
coalition of law enforcement
shitting
multicultural bricks.
Look, I gots no love
for them sand niggas.
I claim black man south central
east side rider.
Well, you're gonna be
the only cat in guantanamo
praying in that direction.
The rest of your homies
for life,
they'll have
their asses in the air,
noses in the carpet,
facing mecca,
and there ain't no calm pills
in gitmo.
I gave no order.
Some "g," unaffiliated,
outside my set, does a deed...
How's that on me?
The shooters were baby g's.
They were kids.
What?
We was watching cnn.
I made a joke.
You know,
you want to stir shit up,
say you riding
with Al-qaeda,
taking flight on a white man.
Bad shit happens to him
or one of his blonde breezies,
that's all anybody talks
about... period, point blank.
You're the boss.
Someone took your joke
as an order. Who?
Some kid called my phone
from the barbershop,
talking crazy shit.
I didn't pay it no mind.
I need a name. Who?
Psh! I don't know, man.
Some little shorty
always underfoot.
Step out of the room,
detective.
What time
did you get this call?
About 2:30.
Hey.
I need to look
at Jamal tillman's property.
Tillman.
Hey! Cut the shit!
Here you go.
Great. Thank you.
Hi.
I'm detective Vendrell.
I need to speak
to Mr. Grubman.
No visits.
I'm the arresting officer.
I just need to speak with him
before his deposition.
Sorry. I'm not supposed to
allow anyone in that room.
Look, we have reason to believe
he may have been threatened.
He recants his previous
statements to us under duress,
an Armenian mob boss
goes free.
Now, you want that
on your resum? Rookie??
Look, you're just
trying to do your job.
Why don't you
come in with me?
Hi, Mr. Grubman.
You're the cop
who arrested rezian.
Yes, I was.
They have you
down here today, too?
I'm always working. I, uh...
I came to thank you
for testifying.
We're very confident
in our case against Mr. Rezian.
Just trying
to do the right thing.
Is there anything else
that we can get you
to make you
more comfortable?
No, I'm fine.
And we'd all like for it
to stay that way.
Okay.
We don't want you to have
any fears about testifying.
We're not gonna let any harm
come to you
or your daughter
down in anaheim.
My daughter?
Well, when we heard
about the death threat,
we took every precaution
to guarantee katrona's safety.
You have my word.
Now, is there
any part of your testimony...
That you would like to go over
so that we're clear?
No.
I'm perfectly clear
on what I need to say.
Great.
I might be able to help I.c.E.
Think locally and act globally.
You interested?
I'm a big-picture gal.
Of course I'm interested.
Look, I got the name and address
of an illegal alien
who's running weapons.
He's a fired
Mexican intel op
who's a possible connection
to a local power player.
Now, this goes international,
be better for you than me.
What's his name?
Aramboles?
Don't know him.
You're about to.
I'd get there now
before someone else does.
Grubman's got a bad case
of amnesia.
What about rezian in jail?
Well, he's still alive,
as far as I know.
Can't really call him up and ask
and hour later,
he takes a knife.
Yeah, well, just have to trust
that Moses' guys
are gonna keep him breathing.
Claudette needs to see you in her office.
- IN a sec.
- NOt you. Shane.
Uh, you beckoned?
I got a call from the D.A.,
said you just visited the
witness, rezian's bookkeeper?
Yeah.
Yeah, my jailhouse chats
with rezian,
he didn't seem too worried
about grubman as a witness,
which didn't give me
a good feeling.
You didn't talk to grubman
about his testimony, did you?
Just to make sure he wasn't
being pressured in any way.
Sheriff's deputy
was present the whole time.
I know.
I just spoke with her.
Grubman's changed his story.
He's recanted everything.
Shit.
Rezian got to him.
D.A. Wants to talk to you,
make sure
you didn't have a hand in it.
How does it benefit me to lose a
high-profile collar like rezian?
I haven't
figured that out yet.
Well, tell the D.A.
I'm available
to talk to him anytime.
Dutch.
Look, I've spoken
to my people twice now.
Is there a chance
that nobody saw anything?
No, see, some people
would rather stay cowards,
keep their mouths shut, and not
put themselves on the line.
You got a problem with me?
Because if you do, why don't you
just let it out now?
I don't konw.
You tell me.
Or you gonna keep your mouth shut
like the rest of these people?
Right. Right.
Unis are saying
that you blame me
because the guy cut out the back
at the army-surplus bust.
Is that what all this
roundabout shit is?
Where there's smoke,
there's fire.
You didn't clear a room, and
a cop could have gotten hurt.
I cleared the rooms
I was supposed to clear.
You want to think it was me
because you don't like me?
Fine.
But it was you
who pulled out a gun today
because you didn't think
that I can handle the job.
Or were you just scared?
Guess we should all, uh...
Get back at it.
You lil b. K?
Who "axing"?
Jamal "axing"
from the joint.
Mal ain't trying to put my name
in his mouth,
talking to no police.
You called his cell
right before he was arrested.
I ain't make no call.
Your number's
on his phone, little asshole.
Look, a number
ain't nothing but a number.
You want stripes
with these 187s,
you got to name them
and claim them.
No one steps up, spook street
doesn't make the top 10.
Maybe one niners start
whispering they're the ones
with bowling balls swinging
between their legs.
Or you go down in hood lore
as the punk who earned Jamal
a 20-year stretch
as an accessory for something
he knew nothing about...
Since the phone call ties him
to the shootings.
Yeah, it was me and my boys
who blasted them fools!
Jamal wasn't knowing.
It was my own ingenuity shit.
My shit!
So, what we gonna do now,
slow man?
Man...
Reppin'
that spook street, my nig!
That's what's up!
S-p-to the double-o-k!
Yo, take my picture!
I merked them slobs straight up!
Spook street!
Meet Al-qaeda's
number two and three.
Want me to call juvie,
or you want to waterboard them?
Hey, Vic,
you got a minute?
Not really.
It's about your daughter.
Cassidy wanted to file charges
against you today.
She made
some pretty crazy claims.
I just thought
you should know.
Said that you assaulted
Vendrell's wife?
You don't buy your kids
a cellphone these days,
they want you dead.
Who else did she talk to?
Just me.
I didn't write it up.
I figured it was just a kid
acting out.
Hey, thanks
for the heads-up.
You know, I got girls of my own.
It's a living hell.
You should take the time...
Talk to her, though.
You're not really thinking
of keeping these people
in the Barn overnight,
are you?
I'm allowed 24 hours.
As fatigue sets in,
someone will crack.
You sure
this isn't about someone else?
Billings may have gotten to me
a little today.
He's selling them food
from his vending machines.
He hasn't done anything
to help solve this,
and he's making a profit.
You deal with it.
If he sees his lawsuit through
to the bitter end,
he's not going anywhere
any time soon.
And send these people home.
If you made one move that
even approached competence,
this would look
a lot different.
You think I don't know
how you and missus feel,
that you want me to quit?
Well, I'm getting my pension...
Every penny of it.
God! Is that
all you want?
That and
the tiniest bit of respect.
For what, Steve?
You give that
to a man... respect...
You earn his hard work
and loyalty.
That's what management here
doesn't understand.
You show a little
r-E-s-p-E-c-t,
and people will do
almost anything to...
Nacio.
The building manager.
Nacio?
You assume people
are indifferent, lazy.
Maybe they just found someone
worth protecting.
Knock it off!
I'm sorry to have kept
all of you here so long.
It's important to find out
what happened to that girl.
I meant to ask you earlier,
how long have you been the
manager of the building, nacio?
This august,
it'll be one year.
Apartment managers
aren't usually well-liked.
Seems like you are.
Well, I made a lot of changes
around the building.
Get things fixed right away,
even if it means fighting
with the landlord.
It's the little things
that matter.
Right.
Why do you think
nobody's come forward?
They don't know anything.
They're worried about
the trouble it could bring.
A lot of them
don't have papers.
Any other reason?
Well, they're mad...
About the noise, the smoke.
They complained to the police
over and over,
but in that neighborhood,
it's tough to get a response.
You told me today
you didn't know anything
about the complaints.
Well, I-I've been
talking to, uh...
The people down here,
since we were waiting.
Where were you
when it happened again?
At the hardware store.
- Rlght.
- Broken toilet.
And then you came back
after the murder.
And you put the bag
with the pipe down,
- came out to talk to us.
- Yeah.
So if we drove you back
to the apartment right now,
you could show
that bag to us.
If I can remember
where I put it.
It's been a crazy day.
There's an old saying,
nacio...
If you never lie, you never
have to remember anything.
I don't think
you meant to kill lana.
Look, it was your building.
You worked hard to keep it nice.
Probably asked those rockers
politely.
But they didn't listen,
did they?
What were you trying to do with
the cinder block, scare them?
You killed someone, nacio.
You didn't intend to...
But you did.
And all those people out there
aren't talking for one reason.
Because you're the only guy that
makes their lives any better.
Isn't it time
to send those people home?
Where's the boy's mother?
Sucking your man's dick
'cause you won't, bitch.
I've advised my client
not to answer any questions.
Shit, nigga,
I got something to say.
We smoked them fools
all day long,
all three of them.
Why?
Just paying the white devil
his due.
No more talk.
You working
my last nerve, nigga.
We was bringing the ghetto
heisman back to spook street.
Like back in the day.
You realize
that killing innocent people
because of the color
of their skin is a hate crime?
You say it
like I give a shit, nigga.
Haters taught hate.
That's why I bang it.
This word
you're so fond of using...
You're one of them "n-word"
type of bitches, huh?
You use that word,
you turn a person into a thing.
Makes it easier for you to
rob them, hate them, kill them.
Do I got to listen
to this church up in here
from this nigga bitch?!
Do you realize how many
black folks have fought and died
to give us the opportunity
they never had?!
Mm, four? Five?
Not only
have you taken innocent lives,
but you turned yourself
into a thing.
You can't
even say the word, bitch.
White man even got you talking
by his rules now.
Straight up.
I wouldn't
waste the word "nigger"
on someone
as empty and godless as you.
Too many of our people
have died
being treated like niggers...
For me to belittle
their suffering.
Yo, just make sure
the streets know
spook street nigs
merked them devils!
They're filing a complaint
against me?
They're alleging that you used
a racist epithet
to intimidate
and harass the suspect.
- IT didn't happen.
- THe lawyer said he witnessed it.
Oh, he's taking what I said
completely out of context.
So, you did use the word.
Some crack-baby tweener
does a triple homicide,
and I'm the one
being held over a barrel?
You let him get to you.
Listen, all that's gonna
come of this
is a rainforest worth
of paperwork
and some chest-thumping.
At my expense.
I'll look at it for you.
You ever feel like you're being
pulled right back into something
that you have worked so hard for
for so long...
Don't even go there.
I got to work out a plea.
The defendant dumped
boiling water on her baby
because the father came home
with a hickey on his neck.
Tell Mackey and his guys
good collar.
Hey.
That had to hurt.
Everything hurts.
New meds doing anything?
Beside the fact they make you
want to jump out of your skin.
I heard your guy confessed.
Yeah??
Brass have to be pleased
to get these killer kids
off the street.
No, no,
they're too busy
trying to plot how to hang me
out to dry for being a racist.
Deflect attention from their
Al-qaeda thing not panning out.
So, uh,
you're a racist now?
How's that
working out for you?
Those are federal agents
finding your arsenal
of illegal weapons.
With enhancements, that ought
to earn you 18 to 25 years.
On another front,
your boss thinks
you sold his blackmail intel
to the armenians.
That's the definition
of a bad day.
Coyote's waiting
to take you across.
Even found you a casa
with a little mountain view.
You like goat's milk?
I got your boss so worked up,
his orders were for me
to shoot you on sight.
You ever
try to come back here,
it'll be a race between
the feds, the cartel, and me
to catch your ass.
Hasta la vista, shithead.
Now we just need Moses to come
through on the rezian front.
Hey.
You and me... we're on the road
to being cool, right?
Look, I handled aramboles
for you.
I saved your wife and kid
from an assassin.
I'm not your whipping boy
for life, man.
That's what you got
Ronnie for.
Mara ran her mouth
to Corrine,
got her all revved up
about this Armenian crap.
I don't need her
starting trouble
when I'm dealing with shit
coming out of both of my ears.
Handle your wife.
And as far as you
making it sound like
- I owe you for anything...
- County jail.
Yeah.
Okay.
I hold you responsible
for this.
Who do you think made sure the
Mexicans didn't finish the job?
I warned you
about the threat.
I put those bangers on
the payroll to protect you.
'Cause those brothers
sure as hell
didn't pull that
shiv-wielding ese off your ass
to fulfill some
community-service requirement.
I want the Mexican
who did this to me.
I don't even know
that the order was Mexican.
The latino crime bosses
need you out of the way
so that they can get on
with their Brown revolution.
But diro is my first choice,
as previously discussed.
And I wouldn't rule somebody out
in your own circle
looking to spread
their wings.
I want who did this to me.
Well,
I'll get right on that.
But the one thing
that we did learn tonight...
I may be the only friend
that you can trust now.
Aramboles vanished.
Where?
It looks like he took the money
from selling your intel
and booked himself
a sea Cruise.
Been a bad 24 hours for you.
You lost aramboles.
Your hit on rezian failed.
He's walking.
He's one pissed-off
eastern euro peon.
He'll be harder
to get to now.
I can help.
But this 30-day-trial bullshit
is over.
I want tenure.
You owe me for your badge.
You got my hearing delayed.
I found out who aramboles
was flipping your intel to.
Even steven.
Anything else
is subject to my availability
and new negotiations.
10 grand a week.
Any attacks on the armos
go through me first.
And no civilians get killed.
Wars are messy.
I like a buck
as much as the next guy.
Can't feel good
about spending it
when some schoolgirl's
collateral damage in a drive-by.
Because you've got morals.
A few.
$10,000 is a lot...
Especially if someone's morals
might get in the way.
A call girl gets a fraction of
that to leave hers at the door.
Then get your answers
from a hooker.
I don't like being told
how to conduct my business.
Only two things I know
about how you make a living...
Employees get well paid
to get their hands dirty
so you don't have to.
And before you raise up
a new building,
the old one
has to get torn down.
So?
So, 10 grand buys you
a one-man demolition crew.
I'll need your answer
in the morning.
Welcome to www.1000fr.com