You going or not?
First, you want to go out, then you don't.
You want to pee, then you don't.
Which is it?
Okay. One last try.
Here? Yes?
Go on.
Hello? Emergency services?
I'm at Pont de l'Alma.
There's been a crash in the tunnel.
I think it's serious.
Hello?
Where are you?
Paris.
Choosing fabrics and bedding
for the Malibu house.
The wedding is in three weeks.
It's our last chance.
I don't know whether to laugh or cry.
The greatest opportunity
in history opens up,
and he's choosing fabrics.
I need you to come
to Saint-Tropez immediately.
I have a special guest I need help with.
-What special guest?
-You'll find out when you get here.
But it's a very special guest.
So come alone.
Don't bring Madame Bikini.
Who?
The gold digger.
Leave her in Paris with her swimwear.
Underwear. Fabrics. Pillowcases.
Raise your hand, boy.
What's going on?
What is all this?
Why am I here?
My son.
I would have thought
you would start with a "thank you."
For what?
For putting her on a plate for you.
Who? What are you talking about?
Wait!
What is this?
Are you out of your mind?
This is the craziest idea I ever heard.
Why?
First, because I'm about to get married.
Second, she's not
in the slightest bit interested in me.
Then make her interested. Isn't that
what you've always been able to do?
Make women fall in love with you.
This is your chance!
Your chance to finally make me
proud of you!