Straight to the morgue, sir?
No. Take me to where it happened.
Pont de l'Alma.
There is no power
nor strength except by Allah.
We retrieved some of the princess' clothes
from Mr. Dodi's apartment.
Gifts she apparently bought for her sons,
and a poem, engraved on a silver plaque.
We believe
it was given to her by Mr. Dodi.
It was a love for the ages.
They were engaged to be married, you know.
Dodi proposed to her last night.
Return the possessions to her family.
I will also write to both the royal family
and the Spencer family.
This tragedy will bring us together.
I am their brother in sorrow.
Mr. President.
Still nothing from the Palace?
No.
But we sent flowers?
Yes.
And letters and gifts? No word at all?
No.
And the poem I sent
to be placed in Diana's coffin?
It was returned.
Without acknowledgement.
Why do they hate me?
Is it the fate of Arabs
to always be hated by the West?
Don't take it personally.
How can I not?
Look. There's no mention of you anywhere!
It's as if only one person died.
But in Cairo, Beirut, Baghdad,
across the whole Arab world,
they are calling me a hero.
You shouldn't look up to the West.
Of course I look up to the West.
You shouldn't.
Exalted expectations are not fair.
They can never be fulfilled.
Did I have unfair expectations of you?
Forgive me.
For failing you.
You were perfect.
No, I wasn't.
Be honest about who I was.
Because wounds will only heal
with the truth.
No, Dodi, no!
Don't leave me!