Hi, baba.
How is our special guest?
She seems happy. Sunbathing on deck.
Good.
Now you just have to close her.
And put a ring on her finger.
Give me a chance. It's still early days.
Then let me spell out what is at stake.
If you were to marry this girl,
overnight you would become a giant.
A colossus.
You will have money and power
beyond your wildest dreams.
And you would finally be my equal.
Your equal?
Really?
How?
Because I would make you my partner.
In everything.
The whole company.
You've never offered that before.
You never deserved it before!
Marrying her would eclipse
everything I have ever achieved.
The Ritz in Paris. Harrods. Everything.
And don't all sons
want to eclipse their fathers?
This is your chance. Don't waste it.
Going home? Already? Why?!
What happened?
She needs to work.
Is everything okay?
Everything is MORE than okay.
I took her shopping.
She picked a ring.
What kind of ring?
A gold star.
Covered in diamonds.
From a collection called Dis-Moi Oui.
Oh my God!
He shoots, he scores!!
-It's an engagement ring!
-I don't know.
Of course it's an engagement ring!
Dis-Moi Oui, it means, "Say yes to me."
My son!! You're a closer!!
You're a Fayed!!
Is she wearing it now?
I need a picture.
I haven't got it yet.
I rang the store after we left.
They have it in their Paris branch.
Then take her to Paris.
I would, but she wants to go home.
No.
Take her to Paris
and put the ring on her finger.
This is the greatest day of my life!!
I knew you would do it.
My son!!
My Fayed son!!
Bye.
Straight to my apartment.
I have strict orders from Mr. Mohamed.
First to Villa Windsor
and then to the apartment.
The Princess has a set time
for a phone call with her sons.
Straight to my apartment.
Mr. Mohamed's specific instruction
was to take you to Villa Windsor.
Hi, baba.
This wasn't a good idea.
Relax. Give her to me.
It's not the right time. Trust me.
The deviation has irritated her.
Give her to me!
Please stop interfering.
It was all going fine.
I'm just trying to help.
Well, you're not helping.
She's stressed now.
Then go and calm her down.
Please, just leave this with me.
I know how important this is to you.
But I know what I'm doing.
Okay, smarty-pants. Bye.
Bye.
Can't we lose them?
Come on. Speed up.
-This is such a mess.
-I know, but I can't do anything about it.
Yes, but you have to try something!
Roses on the table.
-Roses. Understood.
-Lots of roses. This is very important.
Consider it done.
Would you like to see the ring?
-There.
-Ah yes. It is beautiful.
Not bad.
Come on. Let's go.
Make a right.
-Go, go, go! Turn right!
-You can't turn here, sir.
Philippe, change of plan.
Take us to the Ritz.
So,
have you done it?
Have you asked her?
Have you made my dreams come true?
You do?
Tell me.
Are you there?
Are you smoking that or…?
No, I'm looking after it.
Okay.
-Cigars are in fashion.
-Do you want it?
No, I quit.
-You'd enjoy it though.
-Yes.
Next week maybe.
Henri, plans have changed.
Mr. Dodi needs you to drive.
Right away.
Put it on my tab.
In ten minutes.
They'll be out in ten minutes.
-Everything okay, Henri?
-Yes.
Are Philippe and Jean-François
out doing what I asked?
Yes, they're out front
doing the diversion.
No one will see us leave.
Trust me.
Good.
Don't try following us.
You'll never catch us.
Piss off.
-Ready. Let's go.
-Yes. Okay.
Come on. Let's go. Let's get out of here.