Good morning.
Should we shoot it at an angle?
-No.
-There'll be a reflection.
True.
-Opposite way round?
-Maybe.
KOICHI DOMOTO (41)
Thanks.
How do you feel about the camera?
-Oh, I hate it.
-I thought so.
Yes.
Why?
When the camera points at me,
I think things like,
"I'd better be quiet,"
but I'd like to stop that.
I don't think my normal, unaffected self,
the me that hasn't gone through training,
is not worth being seen,
or rather, is not worth showing
through the camera.
Like, what's interesting about that?
I'm not interesting at all.
Even if I put on a concert,
I wouldn't do anything for the fans.
You know how fans often talk
about "fan service"?
I'm the type of person
who doesn't do anything like that.
Well, I say that,
but doing a documentary
and showing my unvarnished self
scares me a little.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
FEBRUARY 2020, IMPERIAL THEATRE
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning, Koichi.
Now, the flight check for act one.
Please go ahead.
The musical Endless SHOCK
is approaching the first day
of its 20th-anniversary performance.
-All right, I'll hook him up.
-OK.
Got it.
OK.
-Good luck.
-Take care.
The flight
is controlled by human strength.
It is achieved through
years of mutual trust with the staff.
Troupe leader, the tension?
-How is it?
-Well...
A bit less over here.
A bit less.
-Okay, here we go.
-Ready.
All right, then. Ready, set, go!
Whoa!
I'm fine, but I heard weird cries.
-Are you okay?
-Yes, I'm fine.
There is no harness
for the red aerial silks performance.
He relies only on arm strength
to support himself.
Always aiming
to surpass the previous performance,
he attempts stunts
that put strain on his body
one after another.
This large staircase is
another such stunt.
It is 4,8 meters high.
The scene in which Domoto falls
from its top step
has always been a major scene.
The two Johnny's Jr. performers
who will be acting it for the first time
are going to try falling
from the middle steps.
This is scary.
TAIGA TSUBAKI
Hold it like this and...
It may be their first time,
but they're still members of the company
playing important roles.
If you hold it this way, it'll smack you.
-Here, see?
-Huh?
Matsu, how about a demonstration?
You got it.
YUSUKE MATSUZAKI
Once more, Matsu. Show him one more time.
Over here this time.
That was great.
Now, let's practice.
MINATO MATSUI
Here goes.
Yes.
-Okay?
-Yes.
You've got this.
I also performed in MILLENNIUM SHOCK
20 years ago.
YUSUKE MATSUZAKI
But I didn't know anything.
I didn't appreciate it.
Like, "What's so great about
the Imperial Theatre?"
Yes. So, I joined 4U in 2006,
although it wasn't called 4U at the time.
Well, I got them to let me perform,
but back then, if I said hello to Koichi,
he wouldn't even meet my eyes.
He wouldn't even say "good morning" back.
That's how he was.
And look at him now. It's like...
he stands out more.
He's really changed, huh?
Koichi is changing alongside SHOCK.
So, we can change, too,
and we are. It's fun.
SHOCK began when Domoto was 21 years old.
An idol taking the stage
in the Imperial Theatre,
with its long tradition,
reportedly drew criticism.
Remember your place, they said.
Yes, how could I forget?
Well, I'd heard he was distant.
It was tough in the beginning,
until he opened up.
He couldn't really communicate.
It makes you feel sorry for him,
doesn't it?
I think he must have been lonely.
Now, with Minato, with newcomers
like Taiga and Minato
he's just generally friendly
in his interactions.
He's able to
suddenly get closer to people.
I bet that Koichi did a lot
of soul-searching to get that way.
He gives you a feeling
like being inside a cocoon of warmth.
It's like, year by year,
as Koichi gets older,
something protective about him,
a kind of broad-mindedness, grows in him.
What changed him so much?
I'm not really sure.
I wonder what it was?
While bearing the title of troupe leader
at the Imperial Theatre,
Domoto performed and rebuilt this show.
Only he understands those 20 years.
Has anyone done
this strength training exercise before?
Like this, at a gym?
Do this part with your pectorals.
Don't do it like this.
They are practicing a dance
that performers in SHOCK
always struggle with.
Hmm... 60 points.
Whoa, you're harsh.
Domoto is pressing
the cast unusually hard.
When you rise up,
think, "Whew, this is it!"
Whew!
I'll say that as I do it.
If you just get up quickly like this,
it will be totally boring.
The dance was choreographed
by a man known for the choreography
he did for Michael Jackson,
Travis Payne.
It's a difficult number
that's also physically strenuous.
My legs...
Okay.
-Last one?
-Two more times. Give it your all.
Two more times. Give it your all.
Hey!
Remember L.A.
You keep going, but you keep
getting sent back to the start.
DOCUMENT OF ENDLESS SHOCK 2012
ASHITA NO BUTAI HE
Domoto and the others learned this dance
nine years ago.
TRAVIS PAYNE     STACY WALKER
They visited the United States,
and Travis Payne instructed them
in person.
Whoa, that was close.
I got on my knees
and begged them to give me a break!
You've got to practice this hard.
It starts once you're exhausted.
When Travis came to Japan
to make his final check,
well, he gave us
a pretty hard time then, too.
I guess that's a funny way to put it.
It was out of affection.
He's a strict person, huh?
Travis is gentle,
but Stacy, who works with him, is strict.
Yes.
"Give it your all! Two more times!"
I was like, "Are you serious?"
It was something like that. So, well,
after we did that,
Travis and Stacy said...
Once everyone was really exhausted,
so exhausted we couldn't stand anymore,
the two of them said,
"After this, we're all family."
And we really were.
It was the moment
we all shared the same pain.
But there was a wonderful sense
of accomplishment in that.
Yeah. Of course,
it was work that we'd done
to make a single production better.
Domoto will join in.
Okay!
That's right.
Let's finish with,
"We should get together now!"
Be careful not to go too fast.
Yes.
We're anxious to get this over with.
We might rush.
FEBRUARY 4, 2020 ENDLESS SHOCK
20TH ANNIVERSARY, OPENING DAY
Opening day arrives.
Thank you for waiting.
We will now check tickets from row six.
Please have your tickets in hand
and do not spread out.
Thank you.
-It's a pleasure.
The pleasure is all ours.
Oh.
Yay!
-It's starting
-Once it starts
-It'll end soon
-We'll go home soon
Okay, it starts today! Endless SHOCK 2020!
Let's do our usual! One, two!
Show must go on!
The 21st year of Endless SHOCK
is about to open.
It's Koichi Domoto's 21st year,
and his 1,732nd performance begins.
None of us can keep up with you anymore!
Tatsuya!
Enough.
You're no longer welcome on this stage.
Come on, Koichi, calm down.
Well, I've got no desire
to do something special
just because it's the 1,700th
or 1,800th show.
So, it takes an amazing self
and amazing mean-spiritedness...
If I say something like this,
I'll be really hated.
I don't mind.
I'm fine with being disliked.
Well... I'll do it as normally
as closing day.
There's a phrase,
"Going home on opening day."
When you put on a show,
people expect something special
just because it's the last day, you know?
I don't like that feeling.
I'm awful, aren't I?
Maybe a little.
No, no, it's just kind of...
Still, it's true,
I don't really want to make
anything special.
You're really always neutral, huh?
Well, otherwise,
I can't do it.
You could call it neutral,
but when it comes to this work,
I'm always surpassing my limits.
Well...
"I'm tired
and it's the second performance,
so I guess I'll cut corners."
The minute you get like that,
it's already over.
It... stops being fun,
and you lose sight of what was wrong.
I'm scared of that.
Yeah, I'm scared.
If it came to that, I think...
the moment I became like that,
I'd never be able to stand on stage again.
You see, the stage...
Yeah...
I think the stage is amazing.
It's like...
Well, it's like that
for the people performing
and for the people watching.
It makes people...
Hmm...
It's like...
Words like "enchant" and "charm"
are such clichés,
but it's more than that.
It's a place where it feels like...
something possesses you.
Yeah.
Well, we have 70 shows to go.
I'm beat.
Still, it's one performance at a time.
I want to treasure each one.
Ten years later...
I doubt you think about it too much,
but do you want to be doing this
in ten years?
I doubt I could keep doing SHOCK.
Ten years...
I might have said the same thing
ten years ago.
When it comes to SHOCK,
I doubt I'll be able to keep it up.
Probably.
Actually, I'm not even sure
if I'll live to be 50.
Yeah...
-Thank you.
-It was interesting.
Thank you very much.
Subtitle translation by
William Varteresian