Last year's summer.
SixTONES 2020 CD debut has been confirmed.
Congratulations!
Big smiles!
They've made it here
with a variety of things on their minds.
My grandma,
she went to the shrine every morning.
TAIGA KYOMOTO (25)
Every morning for more than ten years.
Just to pray that we would make our debut.
She's so happy for us.
So, from that perspective,
making our debut
feels like I'm paying back the kindness
of lots of different people.
And I feel mentally prepared to take
that next step forward.
At the end of last year,
they released a music video
in advance of their CD.
Yoshiki from X Japan
wrote the music and lyrics for it.
Each one of the six
felt what it was like to be standing
on this new kind of stage.
Yeah. I'm right in the middle!
JESSE (23)
We were late to debut,
but I think this is a good time to do it.
These six rough diamonds
are shining brighter and brighter...
as they surge onward
into an unknown world.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
Morning!
October.
With their debut coming in the new year,
SixTONES begin a nationwide tour.
KOKUSAI HALL, KOBE INTERNATIONAL HOUSE
Why have you got so much, Kochi?
Aren't you on a diet?
You're the same.
I can't help it in the mornings.
Why are you picking on me?
When did you get up?
About 6:40 a.m.
-That's so early!
-I couldn't sleep.
YUGO KOCHI (25)
I was like 9:00, 9:30.
I got up at 9:30.
You're oversleeping.
I get up at 9:30...
They arrived the day before.
Whenever they stay in hotels,
they always stay in pairs.
SHINTARO MORIMOTO (22)
Did I snore, Juri?
Really loudly.
By the way,
were you getting up every hour?
Yeah.
JURI TANAKA (24)
HOKUTO MATSUMURA (24)
You did it once every hour
of sleep you had.
One snore per set.
-One snore?
-For real?
Then you'd be quiet for ten minutes or so.
Then you'd get up, mumbling something.
-Did you keep waking me up?
-Yeah.
Why did you do that?
Well, I was kind of making your bed
into a coffin.
This guy!
If I am sleeping neatly in the middle,
you know those long, round cushions?
He puts them next to me
to turn my bed into a little coffin.
It's their first gig
in front of their fans
since they announced
their debut in August.
-Let's make it a good show!
-Thank you!
-Let's do this! Thanks!
-We're counting on you!
All right. Thank you.
Full of individual characters,
SixTONES is aiming for great heights.
The group's debut may be confirmed,
but their provocative performances
remain unchanged.
Make some noise!
All of them have been active
in Johnny's Jr. for over ten years.
These shows, which they perform
throughout the year,
will be the last they do as juniors.
-Morning.
-Good morning.
The preparations for their debut
have also begun.
OCTOBER
SONY MUSIC STUDIOS
Awesome!
Today,
it's the long-awaited recording
of their debut track.
They've all listened to the demo tape.
Can we keep the demo playing?
Play it once.
Can we use the whole thing?
This? We won't use it.
Seeing a record label studio
for the first time,
they're filled with curiosity.
Recording a song here
is another signifier of making a debut.
We're all here.
Ever since he heard the demo tape,
Kyomoto has been unable
to contain his eagerness to sing it.
Wow! The goosebumps.
That gave me goosebumps.
-The vibrato timing was perfect.
-Thank you.
Okay, one more take like that.
Okay.
-Okay.
-Which do you prefer?
Vibrato at the end?
Yeah.
Yeah, on the long "wo,"
and the "mo," you're taking it down.
-Sorry, Jesse, this is the last one.
-Okay.
Depending on if we go with Kyomoto's
natural voice or falsetto,
-our approach here will change.
-Right.
-I want to prepare for all scenarios.
-Okay.
The second half of the song,
when it builds up,
features a solo by Kyomoto.
The original key is high,
and the difficulty is rising.
The song will be better this way for sure.
Yeah, it's cool.
But if I'm performing live on a bad day,
will I be able to do it?
Well...
We'll record it, but...
On the single track,
they'll probably realize
that something's different.
-They'll notice.
-Yeah.
I want to take it on, though!
-You want to take on the original key.
-What do we do?
That's it.
Yes. You're in excellent form, Kyomo.
-Who said that?
-Shin-chan.
-Shintaro?
-That's right.
-Splendid.
-I'm so scared!
This decision could ruin my life.
It really could.
I'll have to do it this way for life.
Challenging myself here could mean
I'll have nights that I cry.
We can always redo it.
Let's do the original key.
-Okay! Yeah!
-Yeah!
When I can't sing it anymore,
it's time to retire.
When that happens, take it down an octave.
Will it be tough for you today?
No, it's fine.
But when I do musicals or singing shows,
too, singing this will be scary.
Definitely.
It's fine if I'm in good condition.
Don't think so far ahead, Kyomo.
-Focus on the job at hand.
-Original key.
-Okay! Very cool.
-Very cool.
Even after the recording,
the members carry on singing.
Their debut is starting to feel real.
Won't it be awesome if this is on karaoke?
-I just thought that, too!
-I just thought it!
What if I'm with friends,
maybe to celebrate the start of a show,
and they go, "Sing this, Taiga!"?
Will I be able to?
Just take it down a half-note.
But I think that's one of the hardest
songs for a young group like us.
-Definitely.
-If we have to do a debut song medley.
I don't remember many groups debuting
with a song like this.
Not in Johnny's.
That's why I really like it.
It works with how people see SixTONES.
-How so?
-It took us so long to debut
-that we ended up as adults.
-Right.
I think the song gives that meaning.
It's great.
It's like...
You associate debuts with youth.
It's something you can't separate
a childish association from.
So, I think it's great that, as adults,
we can release a debut song like this.
That's how I see it.
-Will it sell well?
-You bet.
-Thanks!
-Is it one?
-No.
The preparations for their debut
are getting ever more frantic.
The choreography for the music video
has been completed.
I like that! It's easy to understand.
They're shown footage of the dances
by the choreographer.
-Whoa!
-Cool!
They're totally absorbed in it.
Once the song and lyrics become one,
their expression is born.
That looks tricky!
This piano here, and this piano here.
Then here.
Not too high.
Let's go!
Kochi!
That's it!
Left leg?
Not yet.
-Slowly, now.
-Crouch at the last second.
Compared to his band mates,
Kochi is struggling.
It's like we're moving too fast.
It is fast.
It's only been an hour,
but you've done over half of it.
Really fast.
Show me how to do it, Mr. One-Take.
Though I'm sure it's hard for you, too.
He's practicing during his break.
One more time.
Kochi, it's best
if you don't raise your upper body
too much.
I'm just memorizing it now. Later.
Okay, sure.
Next...
-Want to give it a go?
-Let's try with the music, please.
-One.
-Oh, that's one?
One, two, three, four,
and five, six, seven, eight.
YUGO KOCHI
JOINS AGENCY IN MAY 2009
Kochi joined the agency at the age of 15.
By Johnny's standards,
this may have been a late start.
This town has really looked after me,
ever since I was at school.
If I went to see a movie
in elementary school,
I would always come here.
It's been ages since I walked down here!
Was it raining?
With their debut lined up,
we've invited Kochi
to his familiar Yokohama
for a long, relaxed chat.
This is an old favorite spot of his.
It's hot!
Kochi has been told the same thing
repeatedly since joining Johnny's.
Since SixTONES formed,
people have told me
just being present is enough.
"No, I want to work," I say.
"What can I be doing?"
What do you do
if you're told just to be there?
Was it a shock?
It's not so much a shock...
Is it more just wondering what you can do?
But...
But that's how it is, though.
Nevertheless, I still think
about all sorts of things to myself.
Yeah. About being in a boy band,
about working hard on my dancing.
I've done a great deal of soul-searching.
I'm conscious of the fact that I want
to be necessary somehow.
I want to do my best with that,
but did Mr. Johnny want me to say that?
I wonder about that as I'm doing all this.
SIXTONES FORM IN 2015
When he was unsure
if he should carry on being an idol,
as he'd started college
and was thinking about his future,
SixTONES was formed.
What is interesting is that
we all made the same resolution.
That if it failed, we would quit.
That was a unanimous group decision.
But we all liked being with the agency
and didn't want to quit.
It was significant that we shared
this do-or-die situation
with each other.
If the members of a group
don't trust each other,
you'll just fall apart
bit by bit, I think.
Our bonds won't let something
like that happen.
If SixTONES ceased to be,
it would be awful.
I don't want to think about it.
I can't think about it.
I won't let that happen.
I'll stop it happening somehow or other.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Again.
Each of the members
has something precious to them.
This is going in, just watch.
Tanaka has also returned home
to spend some time with his friends.
Johnny's people always score on TV.
I'm the kind of player who never scores.
But Johnny's...
JURI TANAKA
JOINS AGENCY IN APRIL 2008
Tanaka was in middle school
when he told his friends
he was signing with Johnny's.
That was 11 years ago.
We were really happy for you.
As if it was happening to us.
Weren't we?
Yeah.
I bet you didn't know.
You only knew half of it.
-Right.
-Me, too.
I don't know how the system works,
you see.
-Right.
-Not really.
I thought you were already
fully in that world.
-It was the same with your debut.
-Yeah.
Once you joined Johnny's, it was like
you were in show business.
It seemed like a far-off world.
You were close by, but it felt like
you were somewhere else.
Right...
-Do you know how it works?
-No.
See? He still doesn't understand
the system.
He's only interested in Sandaime.
Have you done Yakult?
-Yakult...
-That was crazy.
Tanaka has also arranged
to see someone else dear to him.
She still comes to our gigs and things.
And she always messages me when I'm on TV.
It really does encourage me.
There's someone Tanaka wants to see.
It must be about three or four years.
That's a long time.
She's come to gigs,
but we haven't met one-on-one.
-There you are!
-Oh!
Wow! Good evening!
-I'm surprised you could tell it was us.
-Well, it's a big car.
Wait a minute! Hang on!
This was my middle school teacher.
-In second and third year.
-Second and third?
I think he's where he is now
because of the choir contests
he worked so hard for
in second and third year.
HOMEROOM TEACHER
MRS. SATO
I'm always checking up on you.
I know, you always message me!
I "like" your posts.
And when your fans post things,
I "like" each one like this.
And she knows I threw pasta
at the blackboard.
-It was the ceiling, not the blackboard.
-Was it?
It stuck to the ceiling!
No, no, I'm so pleased for you.
She sent me a message congratulating us
on our debut, too.
I thought it was so brilliant.
I was so happy for you.
You've worked so hard for so long.
I didn't study,
-but I went to school.
-Yes.
You got along with everyone. You did well.
-I did.
-Yeah!
-You were a regular kid.
-I was.
Just a regular kid.
You seemed to value your friends, too.
Yes, I still see them now.
Are you the le... leader of the group?
No, not at all!
-But...
-Are you thinking of Kondo or Yudai?
-No.
-Who, then?
-SixTONES.
-SixTONES?
-I'm not the leader of SixTONES at all.
-What are you?
I have a role a bit like that.
I knew it!
But I'm not the leader.
The leader of Kondo and Yudai!
My head's just full of stuff
from back home right now.
I'm grateful you've done
all of this, though.
It's all due to everything
you've made so far.
So, have faith in yourself and keep it up!
I've always had faith in myself.
But really, though. Yeah.
Don't forget to be grateful
for everything as you go.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
-Bye.
-Thank you.
-See you.
-Bye.
I'll be cheering you on!
That brought back memories.
A lot of memories.
Nothing's changed in all this time.
Everyone's the same.
On the next Ride On Time...
SixTONES sing a song of resolution.
SixTONES want to be like SixTONES.
And being like SixTONES
is something we won't compromise on.
If it's for the other five's sake,
I'd fight all on my own.
It felt like the dots had been connected
for the final "Imitation Rain."
Subtitle translation by Lewis Williams