FEBRUARY 4TH, 2020
IMPERIAL THEATRE
The curtain is about to rise on a musical.
Koichi Domoto, 41 years old.
He has been the star of this musical
for two decades.
-Get in!
-Hurry up!
-Yusuke, over here!
-Hurry!
One, two!
One more time. One, two. Okay, Got it.
We witness the determination of a man
who has chosen to dedicate
his life to the stage.
Koichi Domoto writes, directs,
and stars in the musical...
Endless SHOCK.
Its history dates back to 2000.
when Johnny's first took
to the Imperial Theatre
with MILLENNIUM SHOCK.
Domoto was 21 years old.
The tickets have been selling out
for two decades.
Domoto is now in his forties.
He continues to perform
dramatic action scenes every year.
Do you feel any resistance
towards getting older?
Not really.
I perform in front of an audience.
That is my occupation.
In each stage of my life,
there's something I can only express then.
I began this musical when I was 21.
I never imagined myself
still doing it in my forties.
Not at all.
But I am.
Why am I still doing this?
I puzzle even myself.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
The musical Endless SHOCK
is a story about young men and women
dreaming of making it big on Broadway.
People! That final stage was great!
Domoto is playing the role
of the troupe leader
who dedicates himself to theater.
It is similar
to his position in real life.
This was the last show after a long run.
You can go crazy in rejoicing.
There are 47 people in the cast.
Each small gesture comes together
to create the atmosphere on stage.
I want you to open up
as you sing the chorus.
I want you to sing and project it forward.
Could you keep that in mind for me?
Got it.
Thanks, guys.
It's a small but important difference.
Please don't forget it.
Don't forget to look forward.
There's so much
blank space to fill.
TAKUTO TERANISHI
Especially for
the Johnny's Jr. parts.
We don't have very many lines.
However, we are present on stage.
It's up to us to fill that silence.
It's a difficult task.
Is SHOCK different from other musicals?
Yes, I think so.
The troupe leader is our director.
That makes things unique.
IMPERIAL THEATRE
November 2019.
ENDLESS SHOCK 20TH ANNIVERSARY
PRESS CONFERENCE
Since Domoto is the director,
there's a question that he is always asked
before the run begins.
I'm sure this question will come up later,
"Do you have anything new planned
for this show?"
Let me answer that now. No, I do not.
Since 2019, they have increased the size
of the orchestra.
The music is now richer and more dramatic.
The next production must be better
than the last.
Domoto has come up
with new improvements each year.
MUSIC DIRECTOR
MASAHIRO HASEGAWA
The high notes... What's my cue?
"When you lose sight
of your surroundings."
-Start right then?
-Yes.
That scene where you start singing,
"Fearlessly..."
ACTRESS
BIBARI MAEDA
We have an idea.
We want to add some music.
-We want unease.
-I see.
Shall we try?
When it comes to that line...
I get it. Understood.
After a note like this,
you will start singing your song.
-This sound?
-That's your cue.
-We're still working on it.
-I get the idea.
There will be sounds like this.
Then you will start your song.
You move away during these?
-Yes.
-I understand.
I like the first note,
but the rest is too much.
-It's too nervous?
-Yes.
-Too suspenseful?
-Yeah.
-The following notes.
-Gotcha.
That's a bit...
-Too much?
-Yes.
Not like this?
Suspenseful.
How about this?
Then start the song.
Let's keep it simple.
Let's try it.
If performing on a larger stage
will be to our benefit,
I am willing to give it a shot.
You will? Great!
If that's what you want,
I am here to support you all the way!
Koichi? Is something the matter?
No... I'm fine.
When you lose sight of things,
you're done for.
-Does that work for you?
-Absolutely.
-It works.
-They like it?
They who?
Who are you talking about?
From the actor's point of view,
I felt that the music
portrays my feelings well.
I'll take note.
Can you write it in here
so that the orchestra knows, too?
These are all tiny differences.
Uh...
The media often asks me these questions
in interviews.
"How will you evolve?"
"What changes will you make?"
I fully understand why they want
to ask me that.
But what is evolution?
Do I have to make changes?
Those are my honest reactions
to those questions.
It'll be obvious if we change the music.
But, I'm more interested in the details.
Sometimes the smallest adjustments
in timing
can be much more important.
Even if I tell the media that, though,
they won't find it interesting.
What will they say?
"That doesn't give me an article."
"We're turning on the light in this scene
half a second faster than before."
"So what?"
That's what happens
when you have a long run.
What is evolution?
What does it mean to be "new"?
You seem so happy, Bibari.
I love the stage.
Each year, Koichi brings us something new.
Each year, I am excited to find out
what he will come up with.
One step at a time, he is trying
to form a musical style created in Japan.
I admire his hard work and attitude.
That's why I want to go along
for the ride with him.
Do you want a larger part?
I do!
I want to have more dance scenes.
The enthusiasm of the cast
fills in the blank space in the script.
The motivation of the troupe lies
in the dedication to this show
as shown by their troupe leader.
How are you going to take responsibility?
We still have a second act!
You think we can do a second act
like this?
Enough.
The stage has a life of its own.
It's up to us to tame it.
No. Professionals do exactly
as they're required to.
Stop it.
Have you ever heard Koichi complain?
This scene,
where a crew member erupts with anger,
is crucial to the story development.
That's why I'm warning him now!
Tatsuya.
Tatsuya Ueda was chosen
to play Domoto's rival for the first time.
We've lost all respect!
Tatsuya!
Enough.
You're no longer welcome on this stage.
Isn't my character making a good point?
He is.
Right?
-A very good point.
-I thought so.
Tatsuya is actually being very reasonable.
In a way,
it's Koichi that's running out of control.
That's the intention of the script.
I wrote the script
so that they're both being reasonable.
Which way do you think
I should portray him?
Should Tatsuya be a little immature?
No, I don't think that's necessary.
-So, I'm totally reasonable.
-That's right.
The actors discuss things
to add more depth to the story.
In a way, Koichi is abusing his power.
Yes. I think you're right.
-Tatsuya is very reasonable.
-You are.
"I don't get it.
I don't get it,
but this is what the script says.
I'll just read it as it's written."
That's the most boring way to act.
To be honest, that's how I was
when I first started on SHOCK.
I hated that, so I took an active director
and screenplay role from 2005 onwards.
What's the best way to express this?
I'm not criticizing Mr. Johnny at all.
Mr. Johnny was a visionary.
He was leaps and bounds ahead
of what I could ever imagine.
Yeah.
SHOW GEKI SHOCK
SHOCK is a show that was originally
written and directed by Johnny Kitagawa.
It focused on action and illusion shows
over the storyline.
However, in 2005,
Domoto rewrote the story,
and he decided to
direct the production, too.
This was the beginning of
the Endless SHOCK that is performed today.
It is a story of conflict and strife
for young people in showbiz.
Enough.
You dance and sing for naught
if you lose sight of what's important.
"Show must go on."
No matter what happens, it must continue.
The flashy performances were replaced
with ones that embodied the lives
of the characters.
The show won wide acclaim.
2008: WON KAZUO KIKUTA THEATRE AWARD
2019: JAPAN'S MOST PERFORMED
SOLO-STAR MUSICAL
For 20 years,
Domoto has dedicated himself
as a stage performer
to this one production.
You have many opportunities
aside from SHOCK to choose from.
Do you not wish to perform in other shows?
You're right. There are other shows.
I was finally able to do Knight's Tale.
MUSICAL KNIGHT'S TALE (2018)
STARRING KOICHI DOMOTO, YOSHIO INOUE
I was able to do that,
but SHOCK became too famous.
So, since about ten years ago,
I've asked to do other gigs.
However, I was told that I represent SHOCK
and the Imperial Theatre.
Therefore, if I did something else,
I'd be tainting their names.
Was that a dilemma?
For a while, it was a dilemma for me.
Yes.
I tried to convince myself
that it was a privileged dilemma.
Yeah.
Most people don't get to perform
in the Imperial Theatre even if they want.
I was suddenly offered that chance.
Yet, I wanted to do more?
Sure, that was selfish of me.
At least, that was what I tried
to make myself think.
Yeah.
Do you acknowledge yourself?
Have you ever acknowledged yourself?
Acknowledge...
I don't know about acknowledging.
However,
I've decided to be proud of myself.
For example, Mr. Johnny always told us
to do something
that only we can accomplish.
He always kept saying that to us.
In a way, I think SHOCK is something
that only we can do.
I am proud of that.
Domoto is on a mission
to do something only they can accomplish.
The sword battle is one of the highlights
of the show.
Twenty-two cast members fight
for 15 minutes with all their might.
It is the result of pursuing a scene
that would be unique to Endless SHOCK.
I want people to love the show.
I want everyone to be fans of SHOCK.
That's all.
I've never wanted the attention
for myself.
If there ever comes a time when I retire,
would the musical SHOCK also end with me?
Really?
Is that acceptable?
If that were the end of this show,
I would start questioning myself.
If this show is going to end with me,
what have I been doing this for?
Koichi!
Thanks. Let's take a 30-minute break
like the real show.
We will resume and start Act Two
from 6:30 p.m.
I'm so sorry.
Domoto is the troupe leader and director.
Can I use your pen?
Sure, but that's not my pen.
It's not?
I can't write because my hand is shaking.
He is about create yet another year
of Endless SHOCK.
On the next episode,
we continue following Koichi Domoto.
You plunge in.
But you have to halt your movement.
This year's Endless SHOCK
is about to begin.
Regarding this show,
I know that the next few months
are going to be hell for me.
Let's do our usual!
One, two!
Show must go on!
Subtitle translation by Natsuka Koshimi