TOKYO
For them, it's a place
where they improve themselves.
Every day, vast numbers
of young people gather here.
Their dream is to live the life
of an idol in the spotlight.
From elementary school kids
to groups in their twenties
nearly ready to debut,
they're all rivals.
If they don't excel in one thing,
be it singing, dancing or something else,
their road ends here.
7 MEN SAMURAI
Among them,
eagerly looking for something
only they have,
are these young men.
Their name? Bi Shonen.
It's incredible. There are so many people.
We'll be okay.
We're all strong. Tough.
TAISHO IWASAKI
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
JOHNNY'S GINZA 2019
THEATRE CREATION
This year,
these six have been active
under the new unit name "Bi Shonen"
after it was bestowed on them.
Yeah, Theatre Creation!
They stand out for five of the six
still being in high school,
and for all of the members
possessing graceful, shapely looks.
-Bi Shonen!
They've quickly established
a dedicated fan base.
However...
WHAT MAKES BI SHONEN UNIQUE?
Something only Bi Shonen has?
NAOKI FUJII
I'm not sure.
I wonder.
I don't know.
Something only Bi Shonen has?
YUTO NASU
Let me think.
This is their reality.
SOMETHING ONLY THEY HAVE
They'll spend these days looking
for something only they have.
I want you to come more forward here.
Oh, I messed up.
How long will it take you to realize?
This is crazy.
I'll give it my all.
JOHNNY'S JR. 8/8 MATSURI
TOKYO DOME KARA HAJIMARU
August. They stand on Tokyo Dome's stage
for the first time.
One member must work out
how they can convey their emotions.
A task bigger than any other.
In search of the answer to that question,
they've come to the holy land
of entertainment, the United States.
Oh, man. I'm scared. Crazy scared.
It's a stage
that can be considered
the starting point of the person
who fostered their careers.
JUNE 10
June.
In preparation for their two-week long
public performances this summer,
Bi Shonen has begun their rehearsals.
-We're from Ride On Time.
-Hello! We're Bi Shonen.
Sorry to leave the introductions so late.
Sorry, we don't have anyone in our group
who makes witty quips.
Let's meet the members.
The one boasting the height and style
of a model, Ryuga Sato.
The most cheerful one of the group,
Hidaka Ukisho.
HIDAKA UKISHO (17)
Why are you filming me
practice my singing?
It's embarrassing!
Really embarrassing!
Bring it through.
Not fast enough.
A member in training
to make acrobatics his weapon,
the youngest of the group,
Issei Kanasashi.
I can't believe you're filming me
with two cameras!
But they are.
Let's do it!
Leading the unit with his great dancing
is the oldest, Naoki Fujii.
And there are members like this, too.
I have tests coming up.
While attending an elite high school,
Yuto Nasu also lives his life as an idol.
This is geography.
My exams are in early July,
so I really need to study.
Oh, man! I haven't done anything.
Tanabata...
And the sixth member,
with a member of another unit,
is the host of a TV show.
Taisho Iwasaki.
-Take it away.
-Our theme today is stars!
It's nearly Tanabata, and the night sky...
Here was his response when we asked him
why he was chosen to be the host.
All of a sudden,
the boss just told me to host You.
So, I've had the privilege
of being a presenter since then.
I don't know why myself.
With an introspective personality,
he spends a lot of time alone
and struggles with the showy side
of being an idol.
PHOTO SHOOT
Even for a magazine photo shoot
like today...
Look like you're about to kiss
someone you're seducing.
That's hard!
I just end up smiling!
I know what you mean.
He's always struggled even to smile.
What kind of skills
will this six-boy unit find?
JULY 9
July.
This day is very significant
for their lives as idols.
Good morning.
SHIRABERU J RECORDING
Today they're appearing on a TV show
with some of their seniors.
Bi Shonen will be showing off party tricks
in a mini segment.
Sato has been entrusted with the job.
What kind of skill
is he planning to present?
RYUGA SATO
Shiraberu...
J!
JESSE
The seniors know how to make
an exciting atmosphere, as expected.
You have to bring them in.
Even in the party trick corner,
they really get
their personalities across.
At last, it's Sato's turn.
His trick?
A lemon.
You're not just here
to be in the background!
Of all things, it's eating a whole lemon.
I'll eat the skin, too.
Here goes.
For real?
-That be must be so sour.
-Yeah.
While he's done it at home before,
his band mates have never seen him do it.
It takes about three minutes.
Hoping to show something only he can do,
he eats the whole thing.
Delicious!
If you're going to do this again,
-do it faster.
-Faster, right.
Or else TV shows can't use it.
Sorry. Thank you.
Okay!
As Sato worked hard for everyone,
Iwasaki looked on, seemingly concerned.
You did well to follow that backflip.
Yeah! I was after Noel's backflip.
That was amazing,
and then I just had a lemon.
I think we made a mark, though.
Everything is already...
See you later.
Their hard work
has always been watched over by someone.
But this person,
who raised them up as idols,
passed away on this day.
It's heartbreaking.
I feel a strong sense of duty
to fulfill...
what Mr. Johnny envisioned for us.
We've resolved ourselves to do that,
and discussed how we were going
to keep pushing ourselves.
And we told Mr. Johnny that.
PLAN FOR SET LIST
The summer shows
over a two-week period are drawing near.
What about the size?
The decisions about what songs to perform
and in what order
all have to be made by them.
But "Summer Station" is "Summer Station,"
you know.
Having "Kimi-iro Omoi" in part C
seems strange.
But I think it should be okay in A.
I think it's really important
that we do our old songs.
It's at this moment...
that their rival unit
starts practicing next to them.
They're good.
How can they produce something
that won't be outdone?
While he was still alive,
an important man gave them some direction.
And that was
to incorporate traditional
Japanese performance into their shows.
If they had overseas ambitions,
fusing Japanese and Western elements
would be sure to come in handy,
he advised.
The show is almost upon them.
The rehearsals begin.
JULY 17, EX THEATER
Today is a big day.
In the Japanese-infused performance,
Sato has been assigned a big role.
Passed down the generations,
it's the mask routine.
He must be perfectly synchronized
with the other members.
You two are in the wrong place.
He also has to perform
rapid costume changes.
Will he be able to handle it?
Thank you.
Around the same time, Iwasaki is deep
in concentration in the theater.
He's thinking about
a key part of the show.
TAISHO IWASAKI
Still in high school,
Iwasaki sings a Hibari Misora song.
It's become a staple
of every Bi Shonen concert.
Why this song?
Thanks.
It all started
when Iwasaki made the decision
to live his life this way.
MYOJO SEPTEMBER 2015 ISSUE
He signed with the agency
at the age of 13.
He was an inexperienced dancer,
and not a good talker.
He felt a sense of danger
at having nothing to him,
and had a certain someone
listen to him sing the only song he liked.
I told Mr. Johnny,
"I can sing, listen to this."
So I did, and the first time he listened,
"You're average," he said.
"Anyone can sing like that."
Yet he didn't give up, and took lessons.
A year later, he had him listen again.
And then...
"Why don't you try enka?" he asked,
and I did.
"That's awesome," he said.
I had never thought of doing enka.
It came as a surprise.
I couldn't believe it.
But he didn't have any doubts.
Something like that,
I just had to try it, right?
It was something I'd never done before,
so I just had to do it
and be told if it was any good or not.
So, when he said, "Let's try enka,"
I just said, "All right," and I sang it.
And Mr. Johnny seemed to like it.
The man once said this,
"If they have the will,
and they're a wonderful human being,
anyone will do.
Because they're the only ones running."
JULY 18 - AUGUST 2
PAPA MAMA ICHIBAN
HADAKA NO SHONEN NATSU MATSURI!
The show begins.
Did you guys miss us?
A BI SHONEN ORIGINAL SONG
Just after finishing the show,
Iwasaki checks his singing.
-A bit fast.
-Yeah.
It's subtle, isn't it?
How can they convey their emotions?
With a new task to grapple with,
Iwasaki prepares for the next show.
AUGUST 7, TOKYO DOME
August.
The next day is
the biggest Johnny's Jr. show of them all.
I didn't know there were so many.
OVER 300 JR.S
Over 300 idols
from eastern and western Japan
assemble at Tokyo Dome.
Bi Shonen!
Bi Shonen to Stage E.
Why can I never find you guys?
The top three will be on this camera.
-For "Can do! Can go!"?
-Yes.
There will be countless cameras
trained on them,
and just working out where they are
is an endeavor.
I don't have time to worry about this.
But you won't know where you can look.
Straight ahead.
Just staring in front of you.
This is their first time performing
in Tokyo Dome as Bi Shonen.
It's seriously huge!
This is crazy.
-Yeah.
-But I'm excited.
We want to perform by ourselves one day.
Yeah.
Exactly.
One member is feeling a lot of pressure
because this is their dream show.
It's Iwasaki,
who's handling the vocals
for several parts of the performance.
TAISHO IWASAKI
How can he make an audience
of 55,000 people
feel his emotions?
It really is enormous.
AUGUST 8
It's the day of the show.
It's never-ending.
Iwasaki has someone
he wants to say a few words to.
Good morning.
It's the man who brought him
onto the path of singing.
He'll be singing this man's treasured song
in front of everyone here today.
It was a hit song
for an idol group many years his senior.
"Kimi ni Kono Uta wo."
It's a farewell song to a special person.
Who will Iwasaki think of
when he sings it?
It's a great song.
There are lots of "you"s
it could be about.
But for me,
it's definitely about Mr. Johnny.
I think he will come to mind
as soon as I start.
A lot of memories.
At this moment, perhaps,
he decided to sing this song
in his memory.
JOHNNY'S JR. 8/8 MATSURI
TOKYO DOME KARA HAJIMARU
Were you getting a little teary
on that song?
-Huh?
-When you sang.
Which song do you mean?
What? Give me a break.
It was sweat.
He knows that he hated sappy things.
It's the day after the Tokyo Dome concert.
Bi Shonen have come here.
See you later!
Bye!
They're setting out on a journey
to contemplate
what it is they've inherited.
On the next Ride On Time...
It's so good!
Aiming to be top idols, Bi Shonen goes to
Los Angeles in the United States.
What is key
when it comes to conveying emotions?
They boldly jump into that world.
Also...
Mr. Johnny might be
somewhere in this picture.
They stand on the stage
that was the starting point
of that special person.
I can't break it.
I want to treasure it.
Once they get there,
what is it that they see?
Subtitle translation by Lewis Williams