Ow!
These six band members
are fighting over choreography positions.
It's as if this is a club activity.
Can you scooch down more?
Knock it off! I'll do it myself!
Enough! It hurts!
This is how we roll.
We'll carry on like this
for about ten minutes.
Who are these six
mischievous free-spirits?
They are SixTONES.
They are a Johnny's Jr. boy band
and the first Japanese band to be
chosen for a YouTube artist promotion.
The music video created for this campaign
gained ten million views
in just ten months.
They were called the new generation
who would unleash Johnny's stars
onto digital platforms.
Their performance is provocative
and unlike that of conventional idols.
They have stirred up a commotion.
With a rock-solid performance
and fan base,
SixTONES have been rumored to be
the next in line to make a CD debut.
How do they feel about this?
People keep saying it's our turn soon,
but it's been 13 years already.
It's our 14th year now.
-Are they sure about this?
-Eh?
Will the audience be satisfied
just seeing us?
Don't they want to see
Sho Hirano standing here?
This was their tone
before their debut was announced.
August 8.
The time has finally arrived.
We have an announcement to make.
DOUBLE CD DEBUT!!
They are going to make a CD debut in 2020
alongside their peer Johnny's Jr. unit,
Snow Man.
This is the news
we wanted to share with you.
It has been a long road for them.
-Third sequence!
-Okay!
From before their debut was decided
to when they announce it to their fans...
We follow the members
for those eight months.
Is this an S?
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
May 1, 2020.
It is the beginning of the Reiwa era.
Fifteen thousand fans have gathered
in the rain to see SixTONES.
Good morning.
-Good morning.
Hi.
They have never had a solo show
in Osaka-jo Hall before.
On this date four years ago,
SixTONES was formed.
Who'd have thought we'd come this far?
-I did.
-Liar.
I thought in four years,
we'd be performing in domes.
You're so greedy.
We haven't gotten there yet.
I'm biracial.
We've always performed here
as backup dancers.
That's right.
All of Johnny's Jr. gathered here
to perform last year.
We've never performed here solo.
When I came in here today,
I got emotional.
-It's going to be just us.
-I know.
This is our first time as headliners.
The members have been performing
as backup dancers all these years.
The fans' support has made it possible
for them to have a solo show.
Today is a special day.
SixTONES will be performing live
in Osaka-jo Hall today.
Today is our anniversary.
See? I nailed it.
See how it's hard to tell
if it's a reflection or not?
Each member has a unique personality.
It's hilarious.
Rassun Gorerai.
SixTONES' main vocalist
is always upbeat and cheerful.
Jesse.
JESSE (22)
Beam!
-How was today?
-It was fun.
Shintaro Morimoto is the youngest
and the mood-maker of the group.
SHINTARO MORIMOTO (21)
Have you ever met anyone like us before?
I want to see him.
Intelligent and calm,
Hokuto Matsumura is the brains.
HOKUTO MATSUMURA (23)
It's not turning on.
I think it's broken.
I can't afford a new one.
You're telling me now?
The eldest, but most made fun of
by others, Yugo Kochi.
YUGO KOCHI (25)
Taiga Kyomoto is the main vocal
alongside Jesse.
-Is that gratin?
-Avocado sausage gratin.
Isn't the name alone tempting?
-Totally.
-This is good.
Please watch.
And the central link
that binds the members together
is the unit's MC, Juri Tanaka.
JURI TANAKA (23)
All six members have been working hard
at Johnny's Jr. for over a decade.
Do you do your own hair and makeup?
We do.
We can hire hair and makeup artists
if we want to.
Liar. We can't afford it.
Yeah, we can't.
Juniors always have to
do their own hair and makeup.
You need to get famous
to ask a professional.
Do you style it the way you like?
Yes.
Do you get nervous before going on stage?
No.
Wait, yes. I do.
Of course I'm nervous,
but not so much that I get anxious.
I was nervous on the first day
at Yokohama Arena.
But you see,
I understand how lucky we are
to perform in front of our fans.
It's such a blessing.
For SixTONES,
our fans are like our agents.
So many gigs were brought to us
by our fans.
We were chosen
for the YouTube artist promo campaign
because we got many views.
We're nothing without our fans.
We wouldn't have our gigs today
if it weren't for them.
Our first show in Osaka.
Can you stop making it special?
-Let's stop.
-I don't like it.
It's just another day for us.
Our next stage just happens
to be in Osaka.
True that.
Whether it's the first day of Reiwa
or their anniversary,
it makes no difference.
They always want to deliver their best
for their fans at each show.
Hello? Can I have a squid?
Yes, Zanmai TV!
The crowd loves their MC.
SixTONES have rock-solid skills
and popularity.
The fans are looking forward to
their CD debut.
However, their feelings were wavering.
Today is SixTONES' anniversary.
The fans have been buzzing
about how their CD debut
could be announced on this stage.
However, the members have mixed feelings
about this matter.
Despite our image, we're not that young.
Nope.
HOKUTO MATSUMURA (23)
Yeah.
We hope we're late bloomers.
We're in the midst of our final chance.
Do you feel you've been kept waiting
for a long time?
It's not a big deal.
Let's see...
Perhaps it depends
on where you set your goal.
Yes, it's important
that we have a CD debut.
SHINTARO MORIMOTO (21)
But that's not our goal.
It doesn't matter how long it takes.
You have to keep your eye on the prize.
It's like a marathon.
When I think about it,
it gets me down a bit.
Well, they...
they always ask us how we feel about it
in magazine interviews.
But...
I never know what to say.
Hokuto and Kochi almost had a CD debut.
We came close,
but we weren't quite good enough.
Not quite.
But you got to be in SixTONES.
Yeah.
Looking back, I can see why.
Now, you're free.
I can only imagine the stress
that we would have been put under.
Yeah.
Life can be funny that way.
You're right.
JESSE (22)
We never thought
that things would turn out this way.
No.
This is the outcome
of taking each day at a time.
I couldn't be happier.
Pineapple, mango and strawberry.
Is matcha strawberry any good?
I―
-Yeah, Juri?
-I want pineapple.
Nice choice.
The members do not get hung up
on the debut,
and instead focus on doing their best
at the task that is before them.
Strawberry, grape, watermelon...
Muskmelon. Melon!
MAY 2019
YOUTUBE VIDEO SHOOT
Hi! We're SixTONES!
Look, here it comes.
SixTONES gained further recognition
through a YouTube channel
that started in 2018.
There you have it―
-Janga, janga.
Jaga-bata!
We'll have the narrator talk over that.
Do you want a shot like this?
Like, "We're gonna do this!"
-Not really.
-No?
-Do you want a ten-second clip?
-Look at those speakers!
Guys, say hello.
They are enthusiastic about filming.
We're SixTONES. Thanks for having us.
Eat up!
Fans love watching their interactions
with one another.
Yeah!
Let's eat exotic meat!
-Yeah!
-Let's eat exotic meat!
Jesse.
ABCHANZOO SHOOT
The members are starting to get gigs
as individuals, too.
This is A.B.C.-Z's show.
SixTONES' MC, Tanaka, is here.
JURI TANAKA (23)
This is his first time
on a variety show alone.
He looks nervous.
Yeah!
Thank you!
-It's Juri Tanaka from SixTONES.
-Thanks for having me.
-On two?
-Sure.
One, two!
Whoa!
What's in there?
Ouch!
They must challenge new genres
to hone their skills.
They have learned from their seniors
how important it is to find a strength.
Do you hope to increase the number
of gigs you do on your own?
Yes. I think it's important to do so.
With SixTONES,
we're not looking
to become champions in a team sport.
We want to be a group of individuals
who are each champions
of different genres.
So, I want to do my best doing gigs alone.
Then, I will take back what I achieve
to share with SixTONES.
SixTONES aspires for great heights
as a group of strong individuals.
TAIGA KYOMOTO (24)
Taiga Kyomoto is their main vocalist.
He has a resonating high tone
and superb singing skills.
MAY 2019 PHOTO SHOOT
SHONENTACHI TO BE!
Kyomoto has a laid-back personality,
but he is uncompromising on himself
as a professional.
-May I see?
-Of course.
I recently dyed my hair black.
I wanted to check how it's photographed.
This is my first shoot with it.
-I saw you checking the photos.
-Yeah.
Do you always check
how your photos turn out?
I usually don't,
but I'm not used to having hair this dark.
Your hair color really makes a difference
in photos.
When it's lighter,
I leave a cheerful impression.
When it's dark, I look cold.
I have to be honest.
As you can tell from the way I dress,
I have no interest in fashion or beauty.
Not at all.
I want to shave off my hair,
so I don't have to dry it.
But if I shaved off my hair,
I'd only have few fans left.
Taiga was scouted in 2006
when he was 11 years old.
He was a shy boy,
but stayed in Johnny's
because he liked to sing.
SIXTONES FORMED IN 2015
It's been four years
since SixTONES was formed.
He hopes to reach stardom
with his fellow members.
When people think of Johnny's,
there'll be a group name
that pops into mind, like ARASHI.
I hope one day it will be SixTONES.
I want to make that happen.
We're never quite a unified team.
We dance differently.
We have different strengths.
Our appeals are different.
We need to use that to our advantage.
I want each of us
to develop our strengths.
I think we agree on one thing.
We are traveling together
to each make our dreams come true.
MAY
IMPERIAL THEATRE
In 2016, Kyomoto joined the cast
of a star-studded musical.
He auditioned and got the part of Rudolph,
who is the heroine Elisabeth's son.
MARI HANAFUSA
Elisabeth is
the most coveted musical ticket in Japan.
REIKA MANAKI, YOSHIO INOUE
The cast are all top-class musical stars.
IKUSABURO YAMAZAKI
Taiga rehearses among them
and hones his singing
and performance skills.
This is his third time in Elisabeth,
but he is yet to be satisfied
with his performance.
Yes.
Sure.
I want more explosion in the first chorus.
Got it.
The director grilled him
when he first joined the cast.
That experience is now Taiga's strength.
This is a career I want to pursue
in addition to SixTONES.
I've found my passion here.
Taiga discovered his passion in musicals,
and has been honing it as his weapon.
He is surprisingly calm
about their rumored CD debut.
How far away do you think your debut is?
I―
How far in the future does it feel to you?
I try not to think about how long
it will be until we make a CD debut.
It's my 14th year now.
There have been a few chances
for a debut in the past.
It was rumored we'd debut,
but when they announced the names,
ours were not included.
It's happened a few times already.
Here I still am today.
The moment you think
that it's your turn next,
your chance slips away.
The moment you think
you're ready to debut,
the god of fortune thinks you're cocky.
Then, Fortune looks the other way.
Let me be honest.
I don't want to debut.
I...
Um...
I'm scared of being asked
for something different.
I'm scared of us turning
into someone unfamiliar.
But, every time we've run into a wall,
the six of us have worked it out together.
If three, or four,
or five of us want to debut,
I'm in for the ride.
Yeah.
They have worked for over a decade
at Johnny's Jr.
What change awaits them beyond?
Perhaps if these six journey together
on this path...
they will reach newfound territory.
We have an announcement to make.
On the next Ride On Time...
Finally,
their CD debut has been announced.
Congratulations! Smile at the camera!
What is going through their minds
behind the hype?
I feel like SixTONES has gotten so big,
and I am being left behind.
It's time to brace themselves
and enter the next stage.
Subtitle translation by Natsuka Koshimi