LOS ANGELES, USA
Summer, 2019.
A group of boys have traveled
to Los Angeles, USA.
They are the idol unit, Bi Shonen.
They are on a journey
to rediscover the essence
of entertainment.
Say cheese.
Yes. I got the shot.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
It is a year of breakthrough
for Bi Shonen.
Five of the six members
are high school students.
They are recognized
for their performances,
which are a mixture
of Japanese and Western culture.
-Look at each other in the eyes.
-In his eyes?
Let's meet the members.
Ryuga Sato, tall and handsome.
Issei Kanasashi, the youngest member.
I've never been filmed
during a photo shoot.
I feel shy.
The most cheerful one of the group,
Hidaka Ukisho.
Really embarrassing!
While attending an elite high school,
Yuto Nasu also lives his life as an idol.
This is geography.
I really need to study.
One member leads the team
with his abundant dance experience.
Face forward.
It'll look better
if you bring in your shoulder.
This is the main part.
Naoki Fujii,
the oldest member in the unit.
A boy whose voice is a weapon
unique to Bi Shonen,
Taisho Iwasaki.
On stage, he sings songs
of the great Hibari Misora.
I just had to try it, right?
So I just had to do it
and be told if it was any good or not.
Bi Shonen is eager for challenges
and has advanced over the years.
Now, there is something
the members must learn.
What is key
when it comes to conveying emotions?
They fly to America to find out.
LITTLE TOKYO
A festival is held annually
in August in LA,
where many Japanese Americans reside.
It celebrates the culture of the Japanese
and people of Japanese descent.
Bi Shonen take part in the festival
as an idol group from Japan.
They are scheduled to perform
on two stages.
Is this what it's like to be in a parade?
We could never do this in Japan.
It feels awesome.
AUGUST 10
When the Bi Shonen members
and Shonen Ninja's Nao Oriyama
arrive at their first stage,
an unexpected guest surprises them.
Morning!
Good morning.
-We're Bi Shonen.
-Yeah, I know.
How's it going?
It's Jun Matsumoto of ARASHI
who happened to be in the United States.
Can you speak English?
The reason why he asked
is because the member must MC
in English today.
That's not all.
Yes, it's very...
The stage is a simple platform
in the middle of a plaza.
A bare-bones stage
with no glitzy lighting.
It is the roots of entertainment.
Their abilities are being put to the test.
Incredible.
We're doing a live performance in America.
You're right.
Even the weather is making it difficult
for them to perform
their signature hand fan dance.
One more time!
The wind is blowing their fans
out of control.
Throw it lightly. It's enough.
The wind will carry it.
One, two. Throw.
A fence has been put up
between the audience and the stage,
making it difficult to connect
with the crowd.
How will they build unity
with the audience?
Matsumoto draws upon his experience
to give them advice.
Some of you can go in,
then come back on stage.
-Yes, sir.
Just enjoy yourself and have a blast.
When you're feeling it,
it will catch on with the audience, too.
-The stage will become friendlier.
-Yes, sir.
Thank you for the advice.
He teaches them
that the most important thing is passion.
It is time for them to take the stage.
Some amateur musicians perform
and set the tone.
Bi Shonen must prove their worth
as professionals.
It's time.
The performance begins
as their senior watches over them.
First, they surprise the audience
with a quick costume change.
Next, a performance with hand fans.
They manage to pull it off.
The opening goes perfectly.
They use Johnny's hit songs
to work up the audience.
Still, they do not feel a connection
with the audience.
The members take their senior's advice
and join the audience.
Much of the American crowd
have never heard of Bi Shonen before.
The finale is Bi Shonen's original song.
That's when...
Come on!
A BI SHONEN ORIGINAL SONG
Even if you don't speak their language
if there is passion,
people will understand.
Bi Shonen!
I had such a blast!
Whoa.
I love the audience here.
It's so different.
Incredible.
Their next performance is tomorrow.
Oh, this is scarier than I thought.
The members go sightseeing
as part of an interview.
Whoa!
MAGAZINE PHOTO SHOOT
One, two!
The members spend their days shuttling
between work and practice.
They fight immense pressure
before performances.
However, they are no different
from your average teenager.
This is plain chocolate and strawberry.
They have strawberry.
Here.
It's so good!
Thank you.
Why was Bi Shonen chosen
to perform at Nisei Week?
It all started with Iwasaki.
I told Mr. Johnny that
I wanted to study showmanship
and eventually visit the United States.
Mr. Johnny thought it was hilarious.
He was like, "Are you kidding?"
He then told me to hold on
and started checking the schedule.
He said, "Okay.
If you guys want to go, let's go.
But you better give it
your very best shot."
The schedule he checked back then
was for the Nisei Week Festival.
Nisei Week began in 1934.
He spent his late teens
to twenties in America.
The festival was dear to him.
LITTLE TOKYO, 1930s
The Japanese who migrated
to the United States
faced unimaginable hardships.
Still, they took root in this land.
Nisei Week became a point of foundation
for such Japanese immigrants.
The festival was filled
with the roots of entertainment
such as song and dance
which gave people comfort.
NISEI WEEK PARADE, 1937
The stage Bi Shonen will perform on today
is the same stage that the Nisei Week
was held on in the 1930s.
KOYASAN BEIKOKU BETSUIN
Koyasan Betsuin.
Hello. We're Bi Shonen.
This temple is the family home
that he grew up in.
When his father worked
as the temple monk here,
many immigrants gathered.
And a stage was built
for temple-goers for entertainment
and as a place
to reminisce about their homeland.
The members seem emotional,
standing on the stage where it all began.
He lived here as a child?
Yep.
Incredible.
I feel that we mustn't taint
what Mr. Johnny
and his father have built from here.
I want to pay the utmost respect
to the things and people here.
Nasu will be speaking in English on stage.
He seems nervous.
Iwasaki seems even more serious.
He was preparing
to sing the Hibari Misora's songs
that were recommended to him.
Hibari Misora had actally come to
the United States as a child
and sang on this temple's stage
as part of a tour.
The man that helped in the production
of that tour
was none other than
the man who helped them.
It's time for rehearsal.
Are we ready?
Yep.
Sound check for Taisho.
Thank you.
-Go ahead.
-Okay.
Okay. Thank you.
He doesn't seem happy.
Can you make the music less loud?
Lower the music, please.
One more time.
He sings a few times more,
but is still not happy.
So sorry to bother you so many times.
Can we let Taisho Iwasaki sing
"Ai San San" once more?
Sorry. One more time.
This is his seventh try.
Sorry. Can we do a sound check
for "Ai San San" one more time?
Why did you sound check that song
so many times?
I guess...
This is a different environment
from usual.
I wanted to practice thoroughly
to perform my best.
That's why I couldn't give up
on practicing.
I want to make sure...
that Mr. Johnny can hear me.
That's what I hope for.
That man taught them
to always give their best effort.
The show is about to start.
AUGUST 11
THANK YOU, KOYASAN
They are counting down the seconds.
Iwasaki's song is the first act.
Will I be able to sing?
You know you can sing.
No, I can't. I'm so scared.
First, Nasu addresses the audience.
-Come on!
-You can do this!
The show begins.
Iwasaki has sung this song
for over a year now.
He says that recently he has come
to understand something important.
In the beginning,
I only thought about singing well.
Now, I want my songs
to touch people's hearts.
I want to convey to them
what I'm feeling inside.
The members sing hit songs
created by that special someone
like they are carving them
into the stage where it all began.
A look of accomplishment
is on their faces.
They know that they have done their best.
What does Iwasaki think
of his performance?
I'd give me a two.
Really?
It's not easy to score full marks.
You're right.
This is what counts.
I need to work on it. I don't have it yet.
Everyone loved the show.
The locals came to me
and congratulated me.
You did fine. They felt you.
It is time to head
to their final destination.
The global center of entertainment.
The six members arrive
at their final destination of this trip.
AUGUST 12
Las Vegas.
They watch some of the world's best shows.
It was amazing.
-What a show.
-Incredible.
-Amazing.
-I'm speechless.
It was awesome.
Now I understand the scope of things
that Mr. Johnny was aiming for.
This is what it was.
Even without words,
they do amazing performances.
If there is passion,
you can feel it in the audience.
It made me feel that we have much room
for improvement.
-Our possibilities are infinite.
-Yep.
-We can do it.
-That's the spirit.
Yeah. I'm going to work harder.
I'm really going to work harder.
Their journey has only just begun.
On the next Ride On Time...
Stop it! You're hurting me!
This is how we roll.
We keep going like this
for about ten minutes.
Taking the world by storm
is a group of strong personalities.
They are SixTONES.
They keep saying it's our turn soon.
Well, it's been 13 years already.
The six of us are on a journey together
to make our dreams come true.
Finally, it is their turn to shine.
It's a new beginning
that could change their lives.
Subtitle translation by Natsuka Koshimi