TOMOYUKI YARA (36)
One of Johnny's top dancers,
is a performerwho has continued to
blaze his own trail...
Tomoyuki Yara.
The show which he produces,
THE YOUNG LOVE DISCOTHEQUE,
recreates dances from across the eras
such as break and rock dancing.
It's a new kind of live entertainment.
Dancers active across the world
also feature in this love letter to dance,
delighting audiences.
The source of this
finely-tuned performance
is his inquisitive spirit, operating
at full steam despite being past 35.
-How do you do it?
-Ready? Go!
This is hilarious!
At the same time, however,
he faces the start of the show
with many injuries.
Having backed himself into a corner,
Yara has some secret feelings.
I feel like the second...
No, not the second. I don't know if it's
the second, third or fourth.
But I feel like a period of change
in my life is coming.
I feel that very strongly
now that I'm at this age.
"This guy's part of Johnny's?"
I wanted people to think of me that way.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
Everyone, please.
Having grown up in Johnny's,
Tomoyuki has come together
with a variety of people through dance.
He's known Go Ueki for over a decade.
He has a great respect for Ueki,who's won
break dancing prizes in world contests.
This is BREAK FREE, who Ueki produces.
They're made up entirely of people
who perform across the globe.
Apparently,
they, too, are keeping an eye out
for what's happening with Yara's show.
As I said earlier,
this is the first time I've seen
people from Johnny's giving it their all.
It's rare.
-It's probably rude to say but...
-I think it's true.
Are you including everyone in that?
-Huh? You mean not just Johnny's?
-Right.
Yesterday,
when I saw their shoot,
I thought they were crazy!
-How many versions were you doing?
-About ten.
About ten patterns.
They kept shooting the same routine,
but from different angles.
When they won the award in Edinburgh,
I thought, "I knew it."
I was quite envious seeing that.
-It was something I couldn't have done.
-Right.
Performing overseas like that
is a dream of mine
I'd like to accomplish one day.
At Yara's enthusiastic request,
BREAK FREE will be performing
in DISCOTHEQUE.
I thought that my beatboxing solo
could be something original that Toyo-chan
and I could come up with.
Yara is directing all of the performances,
but for this collaboration,
he'll be attempting their choreography.
-I can do it. No sweat.
-I wasn't sure.
Then this bit is stuck here. Pop it out.
-Here?
-Yeah, your elbow.
-Then...
-Yeah.
Wave, like this.
Once it cuts over here, let it go.
-Let it go.
-Right.
Then push out.
Once it comes down, aim to be right here.
-Then hold this.
-Hold it.
-And in here.
-In here.
-And again.
The point is to always stop here.
Like this, bang. Always stopping here.
And stop.
Then stab your right hand in.
Keep this here,
and put your right hand in.
Still keeping this here.
And go!
Stab it in!
That's it! Wave.
Looking good.
Okay, pantomime.
-Yes!
-Now?
That's it! Yeah!
Yeah!
-You've got it.
-That's tricky!
Very good.
-Like that.
-I think you should do that first.
-That sound―
-Or maybe last.
-That would work.
-Nice.
What's this?
-He looked unhappy.
-No.
-He was being shy.
-No, now!
-I wasn't.
-He doesn't normally do that.
-Let's do that. It's cool.
-You might be right.
They bring together
all the ideas everybody has
to create a complex routine
and structure as they go along.
Then if I suddenly do a move like this
and go straight into it,
-it might be cooler.
-Yeah.
Which do you prefer? For example,
opening up like this, then "bang, bang."
Okay!
The presence of a dance team,
who share Yara's goal,
can sometimes be a little dazzling.
I like it! I like both of them.
-It's becoming a story.
-It is.
I think whichever we choose,
it will look cool.
I like the one we just did.
It feels more street.
That's true.
-I can see Brooklyn.
-Brooklyn.
Brooklyn? Definitely.
It has a sort of basketball vibe.
I was very envious of them.
Those performers.
Of their sort of team mentality.
Every one of them is a specialist.
They each bring something unique
to the table.
As I wonder if there are people here...
who have the same ambition as me,
I realize there aren't.
Because I'm a fanatic.
I can't expect my juniors
to get to that point.
It would actually be a pain if they did,
and I'd ask them to stop.
Yeah.
I do isolate myself in that way.
But, you know,
once I start heading somewhere,
I can't turn around.
No.
AUGUST 1999
When they were Jr.s,
Sho Sakurai went through
the same ups and downs as Yara.
Back then, the two of them spent many days
researching by watching dance videos.
We weren't the guys
who would be right at the front.
SHO SAKURAI
We weren't in the position to be somewhere
where we would stand out.
Not like how Nino or Matsumoto or Aiba
in ARASHI are.
We weren't showy like that.
So, when it came to what we would do,
dance was the only way to show ourselves.
He was the person who was always
by my side through all of that.
So, you tried to show yourself off
through dance, too, Sakurai?
Yes, I did back then.
Maybe not now, though.
Later,
in a unit called Musical Academy,
Yara was blessed with band mates
who liked street dance.
Choosing their own set lists and routines,
they were an unusual unit for the time.
However, Musical Academy,
never managed to release a CD.
Why exactly did Yara choose a path
that nobody else does?
He's invited the cameras here
so he can explain.
Look at that! I'd like to have a go
on a boat like that.
I can pilot those.
-Really?
-Boats like that.
It looks like it's come from abroad.
Since you've come all this way,
I thought I would talk about whatever,
regardless of if you can use it or not.
Otherwise there wouldn't be any point.
Yeah.
I had a big think once,
before I turned 20.
About whether I should carry on
the way I was.
I think everyone does that.
Well, maybe not if you debut
when you're still a teenager.
Well, I thought about it 15 or 20 times.
It was a multiple-time thing.
About if you should carry on?
It was basically like, "I want to quit!"
Yes, I wanted to quit.
It didn't mean anything.
But dance was something
that I absolutely did not question.
That was true when I was in my teens.
I liked this kind of dancing
and this kind of music.
So, in that sense,
I had a strong feeling of wanting
to be involved with that as an artist.
So,
something my seniors often said to me was,
"Do things like that
after you make your debut."
I was always told that.
But if I could do it, I wanted to do it.
What happens to a person if they can't do
the thing they want to?
I would just have to go for it by myself.
That's why.
So, did you have the option
of leaving Johnny's
and pursuing life as a dancer?
I don't know...
It's not that I haven't had the option,
but I don't think I've ever thought,
"I want to be a dancer."
Probably not.
I wanted to master dancing,
but it was always something that
I wanted to do as a performing artist.
"This guy's part of Johnny's?"
I wanted people to think of me that way.
That's what it is.
And I feel the same way now.
That's why... Well, that's the reason why
DISCOTHEQUE has been possible.
Yeah.
At the end of this road
he's put his faith in,
what kind of view awaits him?
The first day is here of
THE YOUNG LOVE DISCOTHEQUE.
I'm full already.
That's all I can manage.
This is why I lose weight.
I can hardly eat a thing.
It's not because I'm nervous.
Johnny's can't be taken lightly.
Not at all.
People will think, "It's just Johnny's
at the end of the day, right?"
That can't be helped.
But if I can show them
that there are people like us
in Johnny's, too,
I'll be happy.
Sitting in the audience
will be dance-lovers who know their stuff.
Even if it's only one person,
he wants to absorb people into the dances.
-We're starting in 15 minutes!
-All right!
Yara has come up with an idea
for before the show starts.
A disco time for just the audience.
Open to anyone who wants to take part,
he doesn't know how many people
will come up to dance.
Will I be on TV?
Thank you very much! If everyone
makes their way to the circle...
Wow! So many of you have come down!
-Thank you very much!
-Whoa!
Amazing!
Please spread out in the circle
as much as you can.
Great!
Very nice!
The audience build up
the excitement for the show.
Okay! Spin, spin! Side, side!
Very good! To the left!
Fever!
I like it!
I wasn't sure what to do...
Now all that's left
is for Yara to enjoy it himself.
I spent a lot of time thinking this over,
so thank you all very much.
-Okay.
-I'm counting on you.
-Huh?
Now, let's get started!
-Welcome to DISCOTHEQUE 2019!
-Here I go!
Take it away!
This DISCOTHEQUE is neither
a stage show nor a concert.
It's a new form of entertainment.
Allow me to introduce
Tomoyuki Yara!
The energy in the room is surging.
But backstage, one member seems uneasy.
It's the youngest Johnny's Jr.
in the show,
Yukihiro Suetake.
Yara has asked Suetake
to find a new version of himself
and show it through dance.
Look for what you find cool.
Like this...
I just want you to enjoy yourselves.
It feels like you're being made
to do it at the moment.
Didn't I say I wanted to see
how Yukihiro Suetake looked
as a lone artist?
I don't get it. I just don't.
-Not even after watching the video.
-No?
And now the time
for Suetake's challenge is here.
Yara came up with this dance battle scene.
Naturally, there's no set choreography.
He can only lay himself bare and dance.
The professional overwhelms Suetake
with his dancing.
For Suetake, this performance
was the limit of his current ability.
Yara's opponent is Go Ueki.
It's a battle of mutual respect.
The days spent searching for solutions...
The future expectations and anxieties...
The passion of the arena
they feel in this moment...
All are expressed through their bodies.
Yara is precisely where he aimed to be
in this performance.
You have to do what can only be done
in that very moment.
I'll keep doing this kind of thing,
and eventually ten years will go by.
So, rather than just doing that,
if I throw out all the distractions
and just pursue this one thing
in particular,
I wonder what will happen to me.
I'll lose some things,
but what I gain because of it
could be great.
And if it doesn't work out,
I won't regret a thing.
That's also...
how I feel.
Next time,
Travis Japan,
who aim for new heights in dance,
are shown a new world by Tomoyuki Yara.
That's amazing!
I feel like my knee will slip.
Watching Yara makes me feel bad
about myself.
He looks so good.
I can't dance how I want to anymore.
Just writhe around.
Yeah.
They approach the apex
of Johnny's dancing.
If I put the work in now,
maybe the future me will thank me.
Subtitle translation by Lewis Williams