OKINAWA, DECEMBER 23, 2019
SixTONES!
These cheers
carry SixTONES into the future.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
It's just the shoes.
Tie your laces, please.
They'll slip off.
Shin-chan and Jesse
didn't have them done up.
SixTONES is just about to debut.
December.
Preparations for the group's tour
of Japan in the new year are proceeding.
Three times forward. Back first. Okay!
-Forward three times. Use your weight!
-Come on!
Weight forward!
One more time! Weight forward!
Stop!
You can't drink the day before this.
Rolling forward is tough.
Is this how high it will actually be?
-It will be higher.
-Huh?
A new challenge.
Everything from now on
is an unknown world to SixTONES.
Go!
One! Two!
Okay, three!
I can't sing like this!
A once distant dream
is about to become reality.
I guess they're from the school.
I was deciding what it was I wanted to do,
and it was here that I decided.
So, I guess it's also somewhere
that I made a big decision, really.
Before the group make their debut,
Morimoto visits someone he's known
since childhood who run a surfing shop.
Hello!
-Long time no see.
-Shintaro! It's been ages.
-You always came here.
-Yes.
I was here every weekday at lunch.
I think I've already told you,
but I'm in a group called SixTONES
and we're debuting on January 22.
Or is it the 23rd? No, it's January 22.
-Thank you.
-Congrats.
That's the main news.
At last!
SHOP OWNER
MR. FURUYA
You've been working your butt off.
I've watched you closely.
I always called you "Mini Tackey".
But when I called you that,
if anything, you seemed to get mad.
MYOJO, AUGUST 2008 ISSUE
I don't remember that.
I don't remember why I got mad. No.
-Shin-chan!
-Oh!
Congratulations! Wow, this takes me back!
-I went, you know!
-Where to?
This is the surf shop family's mother.
When she heard Morimoto was here,
she dashed over.
-With my mom? Oh, yeah.
-Yeah.
Stop that!
-I bet this is nostalgic.
-Sure is!
I surfed on this.
The surfboard he used
when he was in high school.
It has "Shintaro" on it.
Look, it's got his autograph on it.
This brings back memories!
You'd come back complaining you wiped out,
then go back and try harder.
-Over and over again.
-That's right.
It was really, really frustrating.
Going in... Yeah.
Dust is flying everywhere.
Because I haven't worn it in ages.
I left it inside-out on purpose.
You can see how old it is.
Yeah!
I thought he could wear it again
if he stayed the same size.
Maybe I have.
-Maybe.
-Yeah.
I'll put it here
so you can come back any time.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, really.
Oh, my...
-It's getting serious.
-January, then?
January.
-You might be too good for us.
-Don't be silly.
-Once you've debuted.
-No.
Not as long as I have somewhere
to come back to.
It'll be fine.
I'd love it if you fancied some surfing
-and came to show your face.
-Yeah.
Someone will be here.
-Yes.
-Yeah.
What kind of world awaits him after this?
I always just floated.
Like those people.
I was just drifting on the waves,
deciding whether to carry on or not.
And wondering what the future
had in store, too.
If you have no work,
you find out about the world.
The harshness of show business.
The harshness of adult society.
It was only because
I got to experience all of that
that the time where I had nothing to do
was really scary to me.
It was through experiencing
things like that
that my job as part of SixTONES
became incredibly enjoyable.
We want SixTONES to be like SixTONES.
And being like SixTONES
is something we won't compromise on.
So, if they ever do try to change us,
I think I'll put up quite the fight.
I mean, after all I've gone through,
I'm confident I have the answers.
I have faith in everyone.
That's exactly why
if it's for the other five's sake,
I'd fight all on my own.
"Do you like SixTONES?"
I do. Yeah...
I guess so.
There'd be lots I couldn't do
if it weren't for SixTONES.
There are more things that SixTONES
helps me out with.
We're together because we like it.
I hesitated just now
because if I say that I like SixTONES,
I think the other guys
will all say I'm lame!
"I'm out," they might say.
So, I had to think about my answer.
But I do like them. Everyone.
I think that's why I want to fight.
It still looks the same.
She's playing the piano!
An important encounter
opened up his destiny.
Before the debut,
Jesse also has someone he wants to see.
MUSIC ROOM TWO
She's singing!
How nostalgic!
Hey!
-Hello.
-This brings back memories.
-Yes!
It's been a while.
-Do you remember me?
-Of course!
Are you sure?
-I used to have long hair.
-You did?
MIDDLE SCHOOL TEACHER
MRS. SHIMIZU
I'm the one who wanted to meet up!
Yeah!
My, you're all grown up!
Do you remember that portrait?
It's the music room he always
eagerly came to in middle school.
This is where it all started for Jesse.
As I was reflecting,
and wondering where
my musical life began...
And I still have a long way to go.
I remember you
dealing with all the sopranos,
and I was on the edge
with my loud, deep voice.
I don't go by "Lewis" anymore,
but you said, "Lewis, you should
join the music club."
You encouraged me more and more.
And I didn't get good marks in my tests,
but my performing and singing
did get me praise.
That's right.
Was it on the other side? Over there?
I was having a guitar lesson over there.
"This isn't working out.
I can't play guitar," I said.
Then when you said I should play guitar,
it was like,
"I see, and that will open up
lots of other paths."
Here, you can play A minor, D minor
and E7 like back then.
I hate Fs.
Back then...
Minor. A minor.
A minor. This?
Two from the bottom, three from the top.
-Here?
-That's it.
D thirteen.
Ready?
A minor. A minor of love.
I remember that, "A minor of love".
Go one more down.
Ready?
And back to where you were.
-Two, three, two.
-This one?
Three from the top. Ready?
-I remember doing this.
-You did this.
-Good times.
-Yes.
Why do you think music
is so important to you?
Huh, I wonder.
I couldn't live
without listening to music.
When I'm in bed or in the shower...
Traveling...
There's always music there in your world?
-There is.
-That's good.
I always want to feel a rhythm.
-A rhythm?
-Yes.
I do like a good ballad.
Something by Koji Tamaki, like "Melody."
So, you look up to Tamaki?
Well, Tamaki's the best in Japan,
isn't he?
Are you not writing music anymore?
When all of you were still here
in your last year,
I really put my heart and soul into it.
So, since then I haven't...
There's a song by his teacher
that's full of memories.
-Do you remember?
-Yes.
"GUIDEPOST"
Let's see...
I'm so happy you're singing it.
Do you want to do the first bit?
I'll do the second bit.
You were always walking ahead of me
I looked up to you from behind
I just tried to work as hard as I could
Hoping you would compliment me
Looking back now that time has passed
From the happiness of being relied upon
To showing off and feeling your kindness
It made me want to protect you
Take it away.
At some point, I realized
That there's a path both in front of
And behind me
Joined by the bonds of love
Is the warmth of people
Thank you, thank you
-Thank you
I won't forget this path
I'll always keep it in my heart
As I walk on with pride
Down this path
Thank you
I like that.
-What lines do you like?
-All of them, but the chorus is great.
Like an explosion of emotions.
"Thank you."
Simple words,
but surprisingly hard to say.
Thank you. I made it for graduations.
I've recreated the "Be Yourself" sign.
I've always told everyone that.
Everyone has their own unique voice.
Lots of kids come up
from elementary school
with no confidence
saying that they hate singing.
The point of singing is to unleash
all the things you're feeling inside.
So, you should do it in your own way.
I'm sure you'll face
lots of difficult things, Jesse,
but never embellish or disguise yourself.
Only you can be Jesse.
I want you to stay the wonderful way
you already are.
That's my wish.
"Path" in the song can also
mean "guidepost."
There's always an "ahead" and a "behind,"
and you can get lost.
So, when you're lost,
to keep making progress,
you use music to... How can I put it?
To give yourself something solid.
At some point, I realized
That there's a path both in front of
And behind me
Joined by the bonds of love...
Thank you, thank you
I won't forget...
That there's this path
Music is something I really...
We all share it. It doesn't betray us.
Everyone has their own tastes, of course.
We're perfectly ordinary.
We want to show the fans
something different from all
the Johnny's groups who've come before us.
I'd like things to stay like this,
but be a really big star.
It's funny, though.
We got together when we had no fans,
and now we've done all sorts of work
and people come to see us when we go
on hall and arena tours.
It's interesting.
I always thought we'd get here.
SixTONES' debut is imminent.
All of the time until now
is about to take one single form.
All done!
Our fans are always supporting us.
Whether it's magazine articles,
or polls...
It's the same on social media, too.
When we started our YouTube channel,
our fans helped us out so much.
And before we knew it,
that support had created real results.
Thanks to the fans.
I'm not just being nice.
I really... Well, I think
a lot of people feel this.
But I really feel it.
I'm really feeling it.
We've missed out on making our debut
so many times.
I thought we'd run out of chances.
It was really painful.
I couldn't think of anything positive.
There are so many with Johnny's Jr.
who have more talent than me.
What's special about me?
Does SixTONES need me?
To be honest, I'm still unsure now.
I feel uneasy every day.
Thank you for following
six idiots like us.
JANUARY 22, 2020
SIXTONES' DEBUT
I like the smiles.
Up next, it's King & Prince.
They take on a show compiling the work
of the man who brought them here.
I think Mr. Johnny purposely didn't
explain what "show must go on" meant.
They ask themselves the question
of what it means to stand on the stage.
Doing the shows are a sign of peace.
And we can do the shows
because there is peace.
Their feelings for the man
who taught them everything burst forth.
Let's work hard from now on.
Let's work hard.
-How was it?
-I was so moved.
Sights set on the next show,
they devote themselves to improving.
If I don't do this,
I doubt I can go on living.
They forge their path
into their third year.
Subtitle translation by Lewis Williams