NOVEMBER 2019 TAIPEI
A large square in the center of Taipei.
An enormous stage materializes there
at the end of November 2019.
Keep your attention on the camera.
This is television.
On the stage stands
a Japanese idol group on roller skates,
Kis-My-Ft2.
The performance is about to begin.
I haven't been this nervous in ages.
What's gotten into me?
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
Kis-My-Ft2 is a seven-member boy band.
Also known as "Kisumai."
TV SHOOT KISUMAI CHO BUSAIKU
They are famous for their
friendly disposition on TV.
However, that is not their only appeal.
JOHNNY'S COUNTDOWN 2019-2020
In their 15 years since formation,
Kisumai has accomplished a live tour
in five major domes in Japan.
They have been steadily gaining ground.
However, there is one territory
into which they have yet to venture.
Performing overseas.
Their first overseas
performance will be in Taiwan.
The members learn Mandarin
to prepare for the occasion.
How do you say "name"?
YUTA TAMAMORI
TOSHIYA MIYATA
Other groups have performed
in Taiwan before them.
TAISUKE FUJIGAYA
Kisumai must make a strong
and lasting impression, too.
HIROMITSU KITAYAMA
It's also exciting.
What does the future hold for us?
How far will we be able to go?
Even if we fail,
it will be a learning experience for us.
Will they become a seven-colored rainbow
that shines on stage?
NOVEMBER 15, 2019
TOKYO
It is two weeks until their departure.
They are wearing roller-skates
to go over the stage choreography.
-What about this?
-Hm?
-Is this the actual size?
-Yeah.
The members must know
the exact size of the stage
to perform in roller skates.
They want to deliver a perfect performance
so that they can win the hearts
of fans in Taiwan.
However...
What are you doing?
KENTO SENGA
That was one and a half laps.
How many figure eights will we do?
-Once, then stop.
-Just the one?
But we have time to do one more.
-True.
-Right?
Shall we do two laps?
-I think we should.
-Let's try it.
WATARU YOKOO
Let's do it to the music.
We're thinking of going with these.
-Which one for the skates?
-The skates?
Kitayama wants the costumes
to be perfect, too.
I want something that sways
when we roller-skate.
Sure. We could pop something on here.
Something to accentuate the movement.
The members want to embody speed.
It is the key essence of roller skates.
Roller skates were the reason
for Kis-My-Ft2's formation.
TAKASHI NIKAIDO
They're important to us.
Mr. Johnny gave them to us
as our weapon.
The day has come.
TAIPEI
Late-November 2019, Taiwan.
The airport is packed with fans
waiting for their arrival.
When they appear,
a cheer rises from the crowd.
How far will they be able
to spread their name
amongst people
who know nothing about them?
They have three days
to accomplish this task.
Before the performance,
they do interviews with the local media.
Three, two, one. Action.
It's time to speak in Mandarin.
We are Kis-My-Ft2!
You are pretty.
I was so nervous.
You did great.
We ask the local media
what they think of Kisumai.
Takuya Kimura and ARASHI
are very popular in Taiwan.
Newer Johnny's groups are less recognized.
It's time for them to change that.
SANLIH E-TELEVISION
The next event is perfect
for showcasing Kisumai's strengths.
It's a very popular dance reality show.
I'm going to tweak your choreography
to make it cuter.
LOCAL TV CREW
Who was the most popular?
I love you.
You were the most popular.
It's our chance to win overseas fans.
This is so fun.
Kisumai arrives to check their stage.
The size of the stage is
of great importance.
Tonight's stage is inside
a special 100-meter long dome.
This event is a combination
of fashion shows and musical performances.
Kisumai must perform
their songs on a catwalk.
What is this place? It's amazing.
It's like we're in a cloud.
They immediately put on
their roller skates
to test the catwalk.
REHEARSAL
The catwalk is narrower than they thought.
The stage at the end
of the catwalk is also small,
but Kitayama wanted
to show a stage full of speed.
Next is "Come on, Come on. Everybody go!"
The dress rehearsals reveal
that they can barely pass each other by.
It's different from what we're used to.
It's tight up there with our skates on.
I don't know if we can pick up speed.
We'll have to figure something out.
The members will work it out together.
We've got to make it happen.
When we have our skates on,
we require lots of space.
I wish we had double what we have.
It'll depend on
whether we can build up speed.
It is the second day of their stay,
the day of the event.
A press conference is held
before the event.
-I am so glad to be here.
-I'm happy to meet you.
-I'm happy to meet you. Yes.
The members have decided
to use Mandarin for their greetings.
The press conference is packed
with media from all across Asia.
-We are Kis-My-Ft2.
-Kis-My-Ft2.
Look this way, please.
This way, next.
Will they be able to win the hearts
of the audience filling up the dome?
It is time to show their growth.
The event has begun.
It definitely feels
like an overseas event in here.
The atmosphere is different from Japan.
I'm really excited to go on stage.
Kisumai's turn is coming up.
They will use their roller skates,
a weapon that's unique to them.
I haven't been this nervous in ages.
What's gotten into me?
Let's get this stage rocking!
The members skate
along the catwalk fearlessly.
Even if the odds are stacked against them,
they give their all.
That is the teaching of the man who
bestowed their roller skates upon them.
They sing five songs in a row.
Now, it's time to test their Mandarin.
I am here to find
my princess.
Hang on... I've got this.
-I know!
-You can do this!
That's you!
You are my girlfriend.
Amazing! So hot!
-I loved the roller skates.
-The roller skates.
It was incredible.
I'm so happy to see Johnny's perform live.
Of course, I was very nervous.
I was worried
the crowd would not be accepting of us.
But they welcomed us wholeheartedly.
I was touched.
This is what the Taiwanese media
said about them.
"The fans loved
their incredible performance."
Another enormous opportunity awaits them
at the end of the year.
NHK KOHAKU UTA GASSEN REHEARSAL
It is the end of 2019.
Kisumai is surrounded
by the media once again.
Fifteen years after the group was formed
and nine years after their CD debut,
Kisumai will perform on this show
for the first time.
Whoa! You're sweating so much.
We did rehearsals for the song
and MC just a while ago.
We'll bring our best to the stage.
What do the members think of themselves?
We're not a typical Johnny's group
where every member
looks like Prince Charming.
We're all a little weird.
We're weirdos.
It's good that we're all different.
-I'm sweating like a pig.
-You are.
I was so nervous.
They are neither typical nor princely.
They are just seven weirdos traveling
on this journey together.
Three, two, one!
JOHNNY'S COUNTDOWN 2019-2020
It will be ten years
since their CD debut in 2020.
The seven members lead on the front line
while still searching
for a newer version of themselves.
-What? No way!
-You're kidding?
Is this for real?
-Seriously?
-Yes!
THE NETHER, STAGE PLAY
Hiromitsu Kitayama.
I want to know
that I've at least given it a shot.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be able to stand it.
Yes!
Taisuke Fujigaya.
DON JUAN, MUSICAL
Thank you so much!
At the end of the run,
there were tears in his eyes.
I was scared.
But I had faith.
I'm glad I didn't run from this challenge.
STAGE PLAY
MARUMARU NA HITO NO MATSURO
They each tackled difficult challenges.
Yes.
Toshiya Miyata.
You two will make a great couple.
Takashi Nikaido.
Do you really think so?
Yeah, I do.
Here I am!
Wataru Yokoo.
Say it again.
Okay.
What? Really?
Yes. I had a busy day. I'm tired.
Kento Senga.
He's had it rough, living alone
with his brother since he turned 17.
A person like me
doesn't deserve happiness.
-Don't be stupid.
-Come on!
Through this play,
these members pondered
what it means to tackle new challenges.
I want something that I am the best at.
To be second to none in that genre.
If all seven members can accomplish that,
maybe we can become stars.
That's what I believe.
I get to do these gigs
thanks to the other six members.
I can't do anything alone.
Sometimes we may not all see eye to eye.
That happens.
But our strength lies
in us sticking together.
We are weak if we lose even one member.
Maybe someday, one of us will want to
try things on their own.
But I want us to stick together forever.
Even when we grow old and become old men,
I want us to stick together and be tight.
That's my dream.
You're still cooking lame food?
Yuta Tamamori is the front man of Kisumai.
Miyu is so disappointed in you.
I bet.
I don't want others to do what we do.
I don't want them to go crazy
on TV shows like we do.
I want people to be shocked
by what we are capable of.
That's my goal for us.
Idol group, Kis-My-Ft2.
They aspire to be more crowd-shocking
than any other idol groups.
Their journey has just begun.
Next episode, we follow Koichi Domoto.
KOICHI DOMOTO
Endless SHOCK is reaching
its 20th anniversary.
He has fostered this musical
as the chairman and director.
If there ever comes a time when I retire,
would the musical SHOCK also end with me?
If so, what have I been doing this for?
What has he been thinking
behind the spotlight all these years?
Subtitle translation by Natsuka Koshimi