FORGING A PATH WITH DANCE
The issue goes on sale October 23rd,
and you'll be on the cover!
Yes! Thank you!
Very cute.
Travis Japan.
A Johnny's Jr. unit who has big things
expected of them in the future.
Dancing is their weapon.
First formed seven years ago,
though they've yet to make their CD debut,
they've won over their fans
through their performances.
And now,
their first solo show
is getting a lot of attention.
With expansion overseas on the horizon,
they're trying their hand
at entertainment.
Action and acrobatics
unfold at a frenzied pace.
Even their signature, dance,
is entering a new realm of expression.
The choreography for this has been handled
by one of Johnny's leading performers,
Tomoyuki Yara.
Make the world spin.
Make the world spin?
-Like this.
-Wow!
You made it spin!
You just made the world spin.
Ouch!
You're spinning a lot,
but it hurts because your legs aren't.
Watching Yara makes me feel bad
about myself.
Seeing him choreograph,
he looks so good.
SHIZUYA YOSHIZAWA (24)
I'm never satisfied.
And they're the same as me like that.
They have crazy energy.
-On the next one...
-It's wrong.
-Be quiet.
-That hurt!
In the days leading up
to the start of their show...
Hey! Coach!
...a new way of crafting a performance
begins for them.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
Ni hao.
-Okay, everyone?
-Okay.
-Then you pack it in.
-Yes!
That's the speed.
Okay.
It's a tricky genre.
Yara always picks difficult genres.
KAITO MATSUKURA (22)
I'm not good at house
or lots of little steps.
You don't want the dance to beat you?
It's more that
I don't want to fall behind.
Whoa!
-He's very flexible.
-He is.
Some dancers...
RYUYA SHIMEKAKE (24)
...kindly came here from overseas
to give some lessons.
The lessons were about three hours long,
and one hour was stretching.
It was really painful,
and I was suffering.
I hated that, so I did it every day.
-And now you can do that.
-Yes.
Was that in 2010?
That's right.
Nine years ago. That brings back memories.
-I was in the same lessons.
-Were you?
NOEL KAWASHIMA (25)
Loads of people took the lessons at first,
but the numbers gradually went
down and down.
Before we knew it,
there were only a few of us left.
And then we ended up doing a show.
Did you?
It was through that
that Travis Japan came to be.
That was the very start of Travis Japan.
-Yep.
-Wow!
The band of survivors.
We survived.
By the time we realized it, we'd survived.
I'm glad I worked so hard back then.
Travis Payne,
who did choreography for Michael Jackson,
singled out Travis Japan
along with Johnny Kitagawa.
Their fate since forming
has been to refine their dancing.
So, as you might expect,
they've had a long time
to think about dance.
KAITO NAKAMURA (22)
I can't dance how I want to anymore.
-Right.
-So now...
I don't know how my dancing looks
to the people who are watching me.
-You can't tell how you're moving?
-No.
Maybe you should try
dancing for yourself again?
Don't worry about your form.
Come to the studio by yourself,
play music you like,
and see how it makes you move.
What makes you feel great?
Don't worry about anyone else.
Whatever dance you have inside of you,
we can definitely use for this.
-Yes.
-Okay?
Kaito Miyachika is the leader.
He respects Yara
for his thorough approach to dance
and for forging his own path.
For that dance,
if you're having fun doing it,
I'll be having fun watching.
It's about player-to-player communication.
So, as you do this step and this step,
just by looking at each other,
it will give it a whole different feel.
If I could attain Yara's level
of performing ability,
then, as a member of Travis Japan,
even if we take on bigger
and bigger challenges,
I'll have nothing to be afraid of.
That's why...
That's why, getting to feel that up close
in this studio is a treat.
Spending time with a respected senior
is invaluable.
The first song that they'll be taking on
is the onethey most wanted
Yara to choreograph.
-Okay.
-Please will you do it?
-Of course.
-Thank you.
-Can I make it flashy?
-Yes.
All right, then.
Thank you.
When creating a dance routine,
Yara first listens to the song repeatedly
to build up a vision in his mind.
This is tricky.
Every time he's come across
a new kind of music,
he's expanded the range of moves
in his arsenal.
What steps would be interesting for this?
You were telling them to dance
for themselves.
Yes.
Do you have any worries
like they do, Yara?
-Yes, loads.
-Is that right?
I think many people want to show things to
others but lack an environment to do so.
People like that...
do things like go to dance lessons,
or dance in clubs.
They do that for themselves.
But I think it's great. It shows strength.
If you like dancing,
and you don't worry about other people
and just face yourself...
That moment when you
and the music become one...
When you do that,
you see something new come out.
He's spent days facing himself,
searching for answers.
That's what's gone into the moves
he's created for his students.
It's difficult.
Thanks!
The day the whole routine
is put together is here.
Oh, man! This bit!
It's the thing I'm worst at.
It's cool, but will I be able to do it?
Practice until you feel like dying.
-The shuffle.
-Yes.
Learn this shuffle dance.
Yara has choreographed
something he's also newly learned,
a shuffle dance.
Okay!
-Okay?
-Yes.
-I'm fine.
-Do it again later.
-I'll practice.
-Let's do it.
Next...
You spin around.
Yes.
Right, left, right.
Look at the lines on your forehead!
-I can't do it at all. This sucks.
-Is it hard?
It's fun, I like it.
I like Yara's choreography.
So, I'm having fun, but I can't do it
and everyone else is getting it
straight away.
They're skilled.
That really sucks.
It's like, "Damn. Move, feet!"
I'm sure there must be a better way
for me to teach this.
He's doing well, isn't he?
Don't get me wrong, he's great.
Most people couldn't do this.
Are your legs feeling okay?
In addition to dance,
the show will feature
a vast array of performances
including acrobatics and action sequences.
-No good.
-You were close!
All right.
They must master a variety of skills
that are completely new to them.
I don't get it.
There are just too many things
that I've never experienced before.
GENTA MATSUDA (20)
And we're doing something new
again tomorrow.
Everyone is working as hard as they can
to overcome their own challenges.
FULL REHEARSAL
Six days before the show.
They're rehearsing the whole show
from start to finish for the first time.
They've memorized routines
for all 12 songs,
and made it to the end.
Please get yourselves some water.
-Yes.
However, while Yara usually praises them
with a smile on his face,
today...
-Thank you for that, everyone.
-Thank you.
Well...
You just ran through two acts,
but I thought you were really flat
throughout the whole thing.
Let's see.
Right now, it's not about each individual
working their hardest,
it's about the team.
You need to communicate better,
for instance.
Like the moment Chaka and Kaito
are dancing together like this.
I don't see anything there at the moment.
Right now, you're not showing me
how you feel the sound
in any way whatsoever.
"They're working really hard."
"They're going for it with the dancing."
It didn't get past that.
If you don't start looking at
how you can expand
and how you can express yourselves,
you'll all blur into one.
So, shall we dig a little deeper
to make this even better?
If we do,
you'll be better performers for it.
All done.
I was wondering what you made
of what Yara said to you earlier.
Yeah.
I guess...
The thing is...
How can I put it?
He's...
He's right, I guess.
That's...
Kind of...
Yes, it's really...
Give me a second.
I don't really like this kind of thing.
To be honest, it hurts.
He's right.
Yara's done so much.
He's always given us all kinds of advice
while we've been practicing.
And I think as we did it,
that came through today.
He's someone I respect, but...
I don't know how to explain it.
It's...
Just as we're about to start
the real thing...
It's...
We've come a long way.
I don't know.
You were quite harsh on them.
Yes. Those were my thoughts,
pure and simple.
But maybe I said that to them
because they are Travis.
It was a great performance.
But there are different angles
to look from.
Not just from here,
but from here and here.
I think they'll be brilliant
if they get that, don't you?
When they're such good dancers.
-Absolutely.
-Right.
They can do it. I'm sure of it.
SUNSHINE THEATER, IKEBUKURO
The show is looming.
Will they be able
to live up to Yara's expectations?
"I'll do my best" and all that...
Yara is conveying his feelings
up until the last minute.
I'm sure you'll put the effort in,
but have confidence in yourselves.
That's all it is, really.
Thank you.
This really is something I want to take on
with the maximum effort possible.
It's because I felt the passion
that Travis has.
-Let's do it.
-Okay.
I'll see you soon.
-Mind your hip.
-Yes.
See you soon.
All right!
-Thank you!
-Okay!
Thank you.
TRAJYA -NINJAPAN-
PART 2
The moment their eyes meet,
something comes to life in their dancing.
The path cut open by dance is steep.
Nevertheless,
as long as they feel their camaraderie
in the flow of the music,
they'll aspire to greater
and greater heights...
and keep on dancing.
Next, on Ride On Time,
we meet an idol unit whose members
are nearly all high schoolers, Bi Shonen.
I'm constantly searching to find
what we're capable of doing.
Still not armed with any skills,
they spend days of self-reflection.
Singing is my life now,
but it's difficult.
Our debut?
This is crazy. I'll give it my all.
And they make their way
to the United States.
As they ponder the question
of what entertainment is,
what answers will these young men find?
Subtitle translation by Lewis Williams