Let me introduce us to the audience.
Yes, please.
We are a unit within Johnny's Jr.
that is made up of Jr. members.
Our name is SixTONES,
and we have six members.
Our name is written "SixTONES."
It means there are six different tones
in the group.
Mr. Johnny gave us this name,
hoping that we would become a group where
each of our individualities would shine.
-Very nice.
-Well done.
"What is your dream for SixTONES?"
-What?
-Huh?
Wait, hang on.
Even their answers are unique.
Ready? One, two.
-World best.
-National idol.
-Big.
-Super famous.
-Superstar.
-Popular.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
SHIBUYA
It is May and Johnny's Jr. is gaining
more momentum than ever.
A store that sells only Johnny's Jr.
merchandise has opened in Shibuya, Tokyo.
Whoa.
Hi there.
JURI TANAKA (23)
This is incredible.
I can't believe it.
This is a prime location.
Men and women of all ages
pass through this building.
I've never seen us displayed
in showcases like this before.
JESSE (22)
This is my recommendation.
Please buy it. Please.
Jesse is the main vocalist of SixTONES.
SEPTEMBER 2006
He joined Johnny's in 2006,
when he was nine years old.
He has an American father
and a Japanese mother.
When SixTONES was formed in 2015,
Jesse was chosen as a member.
I'm not good with communication.
I'm especially not good
at speaking Japanese.
That's why I want to put it into lyrics.
I want to make it into a song
and make it a piece of art.
It helps me feel less shy.
Music has given me a lot of freedom
as a medium to convey my feelings.
That's why I love music so much.
Most people think of Johnny's Jr...
as a bunch of backup dancers.
But being on YouTube changed things.
It lead to us being on Kansai Collection.
Being a Jr. has allowed us to do gigs
that our seniors couldn't do.
CD debut?
Without a CD debut,
I feel deprived of recognition.
Somehow.
-Your songs would be done at karaoke.
-I know, right?
I often go out to sing karaoke,
and friends ask me to sing my song there.
I'm like, "Sure... Wait, it's not here!"
"Sorry. Too bad."
People keep saying it's our turn soon,
but it's been 13 years already.
It's my 14th year.
Thanks to my cheerful personality,
we can joke about it.
I wonder what's going to happen to us.
Though SixTONES has not made a CD debut,
they perform songs at live shows
and on streaming channels.
They already have ten original songs.
Their activities are no different
from groups that have made their debut.
The only difference is that
they haven't released a CD yet.
-This is perfect for karaoke.
-Totally.
I wish they'd add it.
I want to debut so we can release CDs.
You should just do it.
We should go ahead and do it
behind their backs.
Let's just do it.
One more take, please.
I love the live shows best.
Yeah.
I hope this doesn't come across wrong,
but I do other gigs
so that I can do live shows.
People find out about us from YouTube,
and we make them want to come
to our live shows.
When I do TV shows,
I learn skills from others
and use them to MC for SixTONES.
People see me on TV
and decide to come to a show.
We've always had it tough.
So, I'm not used to things going our way.
When things go well, I'm caught off guard.
I'm so used to running into obstacles.
It gets scary when things go so smoothly.
I guess it's a habit of mine.
We've been with Johnny's Jr. for so long.
The more gigs we do,
the more difficult it is
to believe in good fortune.
June 2019.
SixTONES have been offered a big role.
This could be a chance for SixTONES
to earn broader recognition.
People still get their group name wrong.
We're SixTONES.
Is it a rising or falling intonation?
-SixTONES.
-What? Come again?
-So falling?
SixTONES. They're SixTONES.
-Either way is okay.
-Yeah, it's fine.
We'll still respond either way.
SixTONES, please get on set.
Let me introduce to you
to the members of SixTONES.
Thank you for having us.
Wait, did he get their name wrong again?
And, action!
They're playing high schoolers
for a game advertisement.
Oops. Sorry.
Don't mess up next time!
Please be on standby.
Morimoto, you're rolling.
-Got it.
-If you please.
Action!
SHINTARO MORIMOTO (21)
Huh? Ew!
A bug?
How many legs...?
Eek! A bug!
Whoa... Get away!
Morimoto does improv.
Cut!
Thank you! Very nice!
-Incredible.
-He's good.
Morimoto is recognized for his acting.
-Cut!
-And cut!
He's so funny.
Morimoto was scouted and joined Johnny's
in 2006, when he was nine years old.
He has since starred and appeared in
many movies as a child actor.
BAKALEYA KOUKOU
GOES TO THE BIG SCREEN
In 2012,
he starred in Shiritsu Bakaleya Koukou,
a popular TV drama series
that was also turned into a movie.
ON-SET INTERVIEW
HOT, ROWDY AND FULL OF ENERGY!
The members who appeared
in this TV series with Morimoto
gained attention as "Team Bakaleya."
They are the members of SixTONES today.
THEIR LEGEND STARTS TODAY!
It was on this set
that the members mutually felt
that they wanted to work together again.
However, after the show,
the six members went separate ways.
SIXTONES FORMED IN 2015
Three years later, they were reunited.
Finally, SixTONES was formed.
When we reunited,
For me, it was like, "This is it.
If this doesn't work,
it's never going to work."
If we debut, we will no longer be able
to operate the way we do now.
I... don't think we can.
I want to stay the way we are.
But I also want to debut.
It's a dilemma.
As a rule of thumb right now,
I don't think about the future.
Whatever task is in front of me
on a given day,
I give it 100 percent.
I worry about tomorrow later.
That's my creed.
To be honest, I don't want to know
what's going to happen to us.
The members focus on doing their best
on every task laid out before them.
Their identity as SixTONES,
a group made of strong individuals,
gradually takes shape.
Meanwhile, their chance
at a CD debut approaches them once more.
PAMPHLET PHOTO SHOOT FOR STAGE PLAY
SHONENTACHI TO BE!
Hokuto Matsumura is recognized
for his sex appeal.
HOKUTO MATSUMURA (23)
He applied to Johnny's many times,
and was finally accepted in 2009
when he was 13 years old.
JOINED FEBRUARY 2009
He gained attention
from the moment he joined,
but was unable to make a breakthrough.
I was giving up hope because of my age.
I thought I had no choice but to quit.
That was when they formed SixTONES.
I knew this would be my final gamble.
You were about to quit?
That's right.
I didn't want to quit. I wanted to stay.
However, I knew I had little choice.
I was being given
fewer and fewer opportunities.
I needed to become irreplaceable.
I felt, "The other five will outshine me
in whatever we do.
There's no point in competing."
I decided to voice my requests,
no matter what people might think.
I was only able to learn to do that
thanks to Jesse.
I really owe that to him.
-Is that so?
-Absolutely.
I was always the shy, pessimistic type.
Then, Jesse came around.
He said I needed to speak up
about what I wanted to do.
I was still sulking then.
I didn't take his advice.
To be honest, people around me told me
that there was no point in trying.
But if you don't give it a try,
you'll never get better.
If you don't speak up,
you don't get the chance.
I love and enjoy acting,
so I said I wanted to do more.
Matsumura is working
on his career as an actor
outside of SixTONES.
He is preparing for a role.
He will play the role of a man
who plays wheelchair basketball
in a TV drama series.
Today, he will practice
with an amateur basketball team.
I couldn't get the shooting form right.
You've nailed it now.
I spent the night
at my best friend's house
and asked him to teach me.
As a thank you, I treated him to dinner,
though it wasn't much.
I was practicing like this,
using a round cushion in his house.
All night I was practicing
giving the ball a push like this.
Next, he learns practical
wheelchair basketball techniques.
It's not easy,
but he is thankful for this environment
where he can work on getting in character.
Oops.
Mastering his passion.
That is what Matsumura has been doing,
just like the other members.
Are we ready?
That's how he has earned
his current status as an actor.
PERFECT WORLD SET
Action!
This is a wrap for Mr. Hokuto Matsumura!
Today is that last day Matsumura is on set
to film the TV drama series.
The staff surprise him
with an early birthday celebration.
-Thank you.
-Congratulations!
He is starting to find a path of his own,
away from SixTONES.
I don't know what to say.
Please become a superstar.
I will.
MID-JULY
It's July, and the largest event
for Johnny's Jr. is looming closer.
Just one thing.
You know how we do "SHAKE" here?
The kids auditioning this year
will come on stage during "Darling."
Three hundred Johnny's Jr. idols
will gather
to put on a live show at Tokyo Dome.
SixTONES' members are all busy
with their individual gigs.
I'm on a prime time TV drama.
Oh!
Yep, Mondays at 9:00 p.m.
I'm performing at the Imperial Theater.
With Mr. Ikusaburo Yamazaki.
You're all very busy.
Jesse is overseas right now.
He's being filmed for a TV show.
Hokuto's finished filming
for a drama series.
Now I'm starting filming for a drama.
-He's playing futsal.
-Futsal?
That's right.
YUGO KOCHI (25)
-For work?
-For fun.
Simply as a pastime.
Everything seems the same.
Let's do it later.
However, just a little while earlier,
they were told that their CD debut
had been decided.
The news will be officially announced
during the live show at Tokyo Dome.
Until then,
the news must be kept confidential.
It is time to brace themselves
for a CD debut.
As you climb to the top, spread out.
AUGUST 8, 2019
It is the day of the Johnny's Jr.
Tokyo Dome live performance.
Kochi was filming several shows
that he is a regular on,
and was on set until the very last moment.
-Hello. Thanks for waiting.
-Let's go,
Please hop on. Climb in.
-Phew.
-You came running.
I feel so bad about today.
I...
Everyone worked hard
to let me leave on time.
Usually we finish early,
but today we ran overtime for some reason.
I can't thank the staff enough.
-We have the show at Tokyo Dome next.
-Yes.
SixTONES is on a roll right now.
I mean, you're really gaining momentum.
Many things are in store for you.
-I guess...
-Does it feel surreal?
Does it feel surreal?
I'm going to completely honest.
It feels like SixTONES has gotten so big,
and I am being left behind.
Every gig that the management brings to me
is so big.
I don't think I am fit
for the roles they assign to me.
Let's go.
It has been 19 years
since the last time Johnny's Jr. held
a live show on their own at Tokyo Dome.
The curtain is about to rise.
JOHNNY'S JR. 8/8 MATSURI
TOKYO DOME KARA HAJIMARU
It is the first time in 19 years
that Johnny's Jr. has had
an individual live show at Tokyo Dome.
Hey!
Kochi arrives. The six members assemble.
Where's Juri?
SixTONES' performance is about to begin.
Are you ready to work up a storm?
Were you waiting to see us?
Okay, let's get this rocking! Everybody!
The time has arrived.
We have an announcement to make.
DOUBLE CD DEBUT!!
There was a moment of hesitation
before they thrust their fists in the air.
This is the news
we wanted to share with you.
We ask for your continued support.
SixTONES have watched rivals
and younger members make their debuts.
It is finally their turn.
The six change in silence.
Thanks.
Other Jr. members stop by
to congratulate them.
We'll talk later.
Sorry I couldn't tell you.
The six seem to be lost in thought.
Much is going through their minds.
On the next Ride On Time...
They are at the starting line.
How do they spend their time?
It's time for brand new beginnings.
Subtitle translation by Natsuka Koshimi