This is record showing the growth
of a group of youths.
We've followed them
for a year and a half now.
You were there the whole time?
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
King & Prince are going into
their second year since debuting.
They are making their name known.
They haven't confined themselves
to the classic idol mold.
To improve themselves even more,
they keep experimenting.
This is bad...
My heart is going to give out.
It seemed challenging.
It was a challenge.
The English words all sound the same.
I can barely speak Japanese.
How can I speak English?
Thank you.
In their solo activities,
they continue challenging themselves
to find something to call their own...
-Sorry for making you do that.
-It's nice, though...
...all in order to keep the promise
they made to someone dear to them.
He's someone I love and hold dear
because he changed my life.
I want to make sure
I haven't disappointed Mr. Johnny.
There we go.
Their true worth will be tested
during their upcoming
second-year concert tour.
Bicycles coming through,
please step to the side.
Bicycles coming through.
Oh, wow!
Bye-bye!
June...
They've begun preparing
for their new tour.
-Hello.
For the jacket...
This time,
they must provide their input regarding
their costumes and other small details.
For example...
Everyone has checkered prints,
so wouldn't using silver
or white sequins here, be better?
Like...
If it's too simple,
it won't be much different
from when we were Johnny's Jr. members.
I'm thinking about the end product.
A glittery outfit with sequins
isn't what I'm going for.
-As long as it stands out on stage.
-I can definitely add it as an accent.
-Using a regular fabric will...
-Right.
YUTA JINGUJI (21)
This time, Jinguji is also getting
involved with the stage production.
Let's talk about "Letter" first.
I want to sit during "Letter."
That's what we had in mind.
Yes!
Jinguji, Kishi, and Nagase
will sing "Letter"
at the midpoint of the concert.
Jinguji will play the acoustic guitar
while singing in the center.
You and Kishi will catch up later,
so you two can move.
How will they convey the emotions
behind the lyrics
to the fans through videos?
This is like a letter written
to our fans, right?
We're basically repaying them
for all the letters
they've sent to us.
Doing an animation
would be too hard, right?
-Like...
-Animation?
A story based on the lyrics.
-We can do that.
-You can?
I can imagine it.
Me too, somewhat.
-Ren?
-Completely.
Completely?
Usually, he doesn't come out
to the forefront,
but at times like these,
Jinguji takes the lead.
He's always quietly observing
the entire picture.
YUTA KISHI (24)
When Kishi was pushing himself
too hard while learning
the new dance routine...
Hey, Kishi. You should take a break.
-Your focus―
-I'm fine.
-I'm good.
-Use the restroom.
-Let's go.
-Just once.
All right. For how many minutes?
The one who urged Kishi to rest
was Jinguji.
JUNE 2019
One night, he was at a radio station.
-Hello.
To represent the other members
and advertise their new album,
he's taken time out of his busy schedule.
Thank you.
Would you like to add
any other information?
-Maybe about the tour?
-Okay, the tour.
-Tour...
-All right.
Seven cities, right?
Yes.
Everything he does is to
build up the group.
Hello everyone,
I'm Yuta Jinguji
from King & Prince.
-Yay!
-Thank you.
It's been awhile, Jinguji.
-It really has.
-Right?
Jinguji has wonderful news.
Yes. Tomorrow, on Wednesday June 19th,
our first album entitled King & Prince
will be released.
-Yay! Congratulations!
-Thank you.
Johnny's classic idol group...
There is a reason why he is advertising
so diligently.
It's because he can't forget
the words spoken by
the person who taught him everything.
He gave me very honest advice.
He said, "Once you release a CD,
you will have to start fighting
with numbers."
"Once you guys debut,
as the youngest group,
you'll spend your life trying
to hit those numbers.
Are you okay with that?" is what he said.
Our Johnny's spirit...
As part of the one-and-only
Johnny & Associates,
I want to be able to proudly
show it off no matter where I am.
Can I get the music?
In preparation for their tour,
they're practicing a particularly
rigorous dance routine today.
I can't memorize it.
-It's so hard.
-Man...
It's pretty tiring.
Hirano joined
despite his schedule being overloaded
with movie promotions.
-One more time.
-I don't remember it at all.
There was another reason why he was having
trouble memorizing the routine.
My leg hurts.
In that moment,
if you can't make it, just...
That's true.
Perhaps because of the pain,
he began to lose focus.
Sho, Sho!
He's in his own world.
Oh, no.
Sho's spacing out.
But he must go on.
-Can we start from the beginning?
-Okay.
Hirano's leg pain
is proof that he puts sincere effort
into whatever he does.
CONCERT VIDEO FILMING
We found that out
when they were filming the videos
to use in the concert.
When I was in fourth grade,
I danced too much...
I practiced so much that my bones
were getting worn out.
A torn meniscus, I think.
That's what professional athletes get.
Yeah.
My meniscus was worn out
and I couldn't stretch my leg.
I got surgery,
but that still sort of comes back
when I move too much.
I shouldn't be dancing, actually.
If I don't push myself past my limit,
it won't be a cool performance.
I have to push myself
to give a cool performance.
So, I'll do my best.
Giving the fans a cool performance.
Being an idol is the career
he's chosen for himself.
JUNE 2019
What makes an idol "cool" nowadays?
Here is another member
who is searching for that answer
in his own way.
Hello.
I'll be in your care.
Nagase is now working
by himself as a radio personality.
REN NAGASE (20)
You're staying?
There's nothing more to see, really.
There is.
For Nagase, who is the main speaker
during the interludes at the concerts,
it's a good opportunity to brush up
on his speaking skills.
Want to see it?
-May I?
-Sure.
After you read their names,
if you say thank you,
it'll leave a good impression.
"Radio handle Nacchan, thank you."
Like that?
I see.
REN NAGASE'S RADIO GARDEN
Good evening!
I'm Ren Nagase from King & Prince.
Well then, let's see.
Nagase wanted to make this show a place
where he can honestly express his feelings
without putting up any facade as an idol.
Our very first theme is,
"What is the most popular
girl's school club right now?"
Let's start with fifth.
Here it is.
I see!
Fifth place is the volleyball club.
I'll read the messages we got.
"They have both glamorous bodies
and energetic personalities,
as well as slightly larger breasts.
Even as a woman,
I think they're the best." Exactly.
"Exactly"?
Exactly. The volleyball club...
They all have big boobs for some reason.
I wonder why?
Do they have volleyballs in there?
Breasts...
I like butts better, though.
I prefer large butts.
-Let's move on.
-Fourth place?
I was told to stop, sorry.
"Sha-la-la Hajikeru Love."
Then...
he made one request to the staff.
Please keep the volleyball part.
I'm serious.
But... you said, "boobs."
Is that not allowed by my agency?
They're asking about it now.
-I don't know.
-He's talking about breasts already.
What else am I supposed to say?
"Breasts" is okay.
They're consulting.
I'll leave it up to you, then.
But personally...
Okay.
We got a mild "okay."
We'll mildly dig deeper then.
Please.
I was talking non-stop for an hour.
-This is really tiring.
-Right?
Radio is interesting, though.
Up we go.
Each of them are polishing their acts
because they want to
strengthen King & Prince.
Hirano explained it in this way...
We're like the Avengers.
One is active on variety shows,
one is an actor,
one is a speaker, and so on.
We have strong personalities
and are successful on our own,
but when we come together,
we're very powerful.
I hope we can be like that.
There is one more member
whom they hold dear.
They expressed their feelings
in the video for the concert.
Watering pink flowers...
Pink is...
GENKI IWAHASHI (22)
...the color of Genki Iwahashi,
who is being treated for an illness.
The members have never forgotten
that King & Prince
is a six-person group.
We thought it'd be nice
to show us all
making one flower bloom.
And we also wanted to show that
Genki was participating in
the concert along with us.
That's why we wanted to start
the video with a scene of us
watering pink flowers.
JULY 18, 2019
YOKOHAMA ARENA
And in July...
it's one day before the opening day
of their second-year concert tour.
They will once again
stand on the same stage they stood on
when they debuted one year ago.
-What number?
-Eight!
Amazing.
Seeing this makes me so excited.
The difference is,
they will be using many more
large-scale special effects.
Many of which were suggested
by the members themselves.
It's rotating.
Rotating.
The set on the main stage
is able to rotate
to show two different designs.
The classic idol image
and the mature King & Prince...
Both of their characters
can be portrayed this way.
Can we stop here for a moment
and perform this song here for a second?
Sure.
Almost all of the members' requests
for stage production
have been fulfilled by the staff.
As they go through trial and error,
they feel the weight of responsibility.
-The stage effects are pretty crazy.
-I know.
I mean, the set itself flips.
You only really see
a set flip like that in a theater.
That's why
I think we can surprise
the people who see it.
However,
this time, there was more than that.
-Here we go.
-Okay.
The center stage will spin
above the audience like a giant propeller.
The members will stand on a glass floor.
It's been made so that the audience
can see them from below.
King & Prince, it's time to move.
Will you keep to the right?
-Pick a side.
-Right.
This is when tensions begin to rise.
The members are in the front.
The members are facing us.
Just a moment. Okay.
ARASHI's Jun Matsumoto.
The members of King & Prince asked him
to help with stage directing,
so he is here to do a final check
for his assigned block.
Be ready for it to spin.
Go.
Matsumoto's eyes have been trained
from directing years of ARASHI's concerts.
Where will he be looking?
Is this the actual speed?
Yes, it is.
Go to your bridge positions.
Bridge positions? Okay.
The bridge starts around here.
Ready...
How far each member is from each other
and when they begin moving...
He thoroughly checks how
they will be seen by the audience.
Make sure the cameras
are directly underneath.
Right now, Sho is...
He lives by the phrase,
"the devil's in the detail"
and makes slight changes.
-I see.
-I want it to touch.
Oh, sorry.
I want that part to be a little tighter.
At the end. Right there.
Are there two lines?
-No.
-Three, two.
Three and two?
-Three and two.
-Okay.
Finish in that position.
Okay.
The plethora of things they do to ensure
the audience enjoys every single second,
is what creates entertainment.
You guys shouldn't
look down too much during this song.
-Because the light comes from above.
-Okay.
From senior to junior,
these thoughts are passed down.
YOKOHAMA ARENA
July 19th.
King & Prince's second-year tour
is finally about to begin.
TEN MINUTES UNTIL SHOWTIME
Until last year,
they were still a bit nervous,
but look how they are this year.
Let's go.
See you.
Here I go. Bye.
They've matured this much
thanks to each other and
what they've experienced this past year.
Bye.
That is why...
...they began by expressing their feelings
for their other member.
The stage is rotating.
It's time for the mature King & Prince.
And then...
a song in memoriam.
SONG POPULARIZED
BY THE FIRST JOHNNY'S GROUP
It wasn't in the set list originally,
but I really wanted it to reach the person
who is the most dear to us right now.
So, I added it in.
He sang with the determination
that they will stand on
their own two feet from now on.
We are...
King &...
Prince!
Thank you!
They will once again embark on
a new journey.
Thank you so much!
On the next Ride On Time,
They get a big opportunity
from a dear friend.
They battle the pressure...
Nothing's easy.
It's hard.
And on the big day,
something happens to Kishi's body.
Will they be able to overcome it all?
Meanwhile, in the brutal heat,
other members devote themselves to acting.
I'll survive with fighting spirit.
The promise they made
to someone precious empowers them.
I want to hurry up and make it overseas,
so we can show him.
He said, "You guys can do it."
I'll put my faith in those words.
Subtitle translation by Kiko Morita