September.
These boys have been confronted
by a predicament.
They're the idol unit, HiHi Jets.
They're supposed to be a quintet,
but only three of them are here.
What happened?
I had to consider what I'd do
if the group couldn't go on anymore.
In case it went south.
What scares me most
is that the two of them
might not come back.
After us three have worked so hard.
A relationship of trust.
It's not a question of wanting to have it,
if we don't have it...
I think it's over.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
We are HiHi Jets, and we have a dream.
To be a legendary group.
Their weapon is the roller skate,
which they inherited from past groups.
With ever-evolving performances,
each of the five has a unique personality.
-Come on!
-Ichiro's a light player.
-Hey!
-What?
Soya Igari is the youngest.
He doesn't shy away
from speaking his mind to his elders.
He handles everything
to do with roller skates,
including choreography.
Ryuto Sakuma is a nimble skater who can
even perform repairs on the skates.
That's the color the new ones have.
It looks worn out.
And Ryo Hashimoto,
the kind to put in hard work quietly.
RYO HASHIMOTO (19)
Oh, you made me jump. Good morning.
Specializing in singing and dance,
Mizuki Inoue loves his job.
There's not much I want.
Oh?
I never know what to do with myself
when there's no more work to do.
And then...
Action!
TV DRAMA KOI NO YAMAI TO YAROGUMI
...eager to make acting his new weapon
is the group's center, Yuto Takahashi.
I'll get a girlfriend one way or another!
The other members
are incredible with their technical skill.
They can do acrobatics,
they can sing and so on.
I want to open up more paths for myself.
I feel that way now.
They want to be legendary.
Great stuff!
But HiHi Jets would be faced
with a crisis.
JULY 4, 2019
DREAM BOYS PRESS CONFERENCE
July.
It's been confirmed
the five will be performing in a big show.
Two members from King & Prince,
a unit senior to them, will be starring
in a show called DREAM BOYS.
For these young men
yet to make their debut,
this could be the gateway to success.
Takahashi has been cast as the hero's
younger brother, a big part.
All right!
A major element of the story is this.
Through its depiction of boxing brothers
chasing their dreams,
the production shows the value
of personal bonds.
Cross!
Yeehaw!
He needs to look like he knows
what he's doing onstage.
As you'd expect from such a big role,
he has a lot of lines.
Filming a TV drama alongside this,
Takahashi has been struggling
to remember all his lines.
Have you memorized it?
I've hardly got anywhere with it yet.
On top of that, someone has come
to give him some guidance today.
It's Koichi Domoto, a reverential figure.
Hello, Koichi.
"I don't know my parents. I was taken
to the home as soon as I was born.
But I wasn't lonely.
That's because I had Yuta,
who was like a big brother to me.
I call him 'Brother,'
but we're not actually brothers."
As you were reading there,
-you kept rushing to get to the next line.
-Right.
You tend to say the first bit boldly,
but then trail off.
Right.
"I don't know my parents. I was taken
to the home as soon as I was born."
-You end up speaking like that.
-Right.
Try your best not to fade away at the end.
"I don't know my parents. I was taken
to the home as soon as I was born.
But I wasn't lonely.
That's because I had Yuta,
who was like a big brother to me.
I call him 'Brother,'
but we're not actually brothers."
-You're too self-conscious now.
-Yes, sorry.
Nice and natural.
-"That's because I had Yuta."
Let the audience absorb those words,
and then move on.
Yes.
I learned how to box, too...
Seriously!
Oh, man.
Koichi took the time
out of his busy schedule to be here,
and I hadn't even read the whole script...
I feel apologetic, I have to say.
Ultimately, we have to study.
We're in that stage of our careers.
Thank you very much.
However, he's in
an unforgiving environment.
It's not just the drama he's juggling
with the stage show.
AUGUST 3 - AUGUST 23 2019
PAPA MAMA ICHIBAN
HADAKA NO SHONEN NATSU MATSURI!
In fact, the summer performances
are still going on.
You really hate it. For example...
Their senior idols
have already been through
these brutal days.
...when you're doing a stage show,
you have a huge space...
"Yuta! Haven't you got changed yet?
Come on, let's go home."
-You're too soft.
-Okay. I'll project more.
Let's say he's by that wall. "Yuta!"
Imagine that,
and you probably won't sound quiet.
-Shall I try?
-Go for it.
"Yuta! Haven't you got changed yet?
Come on, let's go home."
That's it.
Picture that as you do it.
It's around this time that Takahashi...
All done.
...gets a problem with his foot.
Is your foot okay?
Well, not really.
I didn't wear the skates
while we were doing the drama,
and my feet must have grown or something.
They don't fit me,
so I just had to bear it
and make it through the gigs.
-It's bleeding.
-Yeah.
There's not much I can do.
I think I've made it a bit worse today.
But I've got to keep going.
Their current roller-skating routine
poses an even greater challenge.
It's this performance with batons.
They pass the batons while skating around.
The difficulty level is high.
Hashimoto, who dropped a baton
while they were rehearsing,
is practicing over and over by himself.
I'm not working too hard. Don't worry.
I don't want it to look like
I'm really exerting myself.
I need to memorize two songs today.
It's crazy.
There are five days to go
until the first show.
AUGUST 28, 2019
Dress rehearsals have been impossible
with the costumes only just being fitted.
This is mad, for real.
We haven't rehearsed at all.
I never thought I'd be preparing for
an opening night at the Imperial Theatre.
It's Sakuma who lifts everyone's spirits.
Every one of them
supports the group in their own way.
Nobody is replaceable.
-I like this.
-You can't wear that.
Why not?
SEPTEMBER 3, 2019
OPENING NIGHT
The opening night is here.
Hey, isn't this awesome?
We could be on TV!
It'll be tough doing as Rika says, though.
Who cares what she says
if we have more places to perform?
Can we trust what an adult says?
I don't know my parents. I was taken
to the home as soon as I was born.
But I wasn't lonely.
That's because I had Yuta,
who was like a big brother to me.
Stop it!
Takahashi gives everything he's got
to his portrayal
of the younger brother
struck down by illness.
Please, stop it now!
And then, the baton routine they kept
failing to get right in rehearsals.
They finish it
without dropping a single baton.
Did you see us nail the batons?
It seems I'm a man
who's good on the night.
I'm just glad we made it
through the first night.
The Inoue Report... Shall I do that?
They'd get through this, somehow.
Everyone was thinking that at this time.
Can we talk to you, Sakuma?
Do you have a minute?
Sure.
Crisis strikes.
Something Hashimoto and Sakuma have done
is seen as a problem.
Takahashi made this post on his blog.
SEPTEMBER 11
HIHI JETS' BLOG
WITHDRAWAL FROM ACTIVITY...
The pair will temporarily withdraw
from public life.
Since then,
HiHi Jets have been performing
as a trio on the show.
Okay, let's do it here.
All right.
Has this pushed your debut further away?
Of course. I definitely think so.
I'm sure the audience paid their money
thinking they would see
all five HiHi Jets,
and made room in their calendars.
Then they traveled here to see us.
I feel so much regret about that.
If they decided to leave, I'd say that
they have to come back to the five of us,
or three, as we are now.
To be honest, if it wasn't for us five,
I don't think I'd be with this agency.
I've always thought that if HiHi
broke up, I'd quit.
So, if those two leave,
I'll go with them. I told them that.
Human beings may make mistakes,
but if you just leave it at that,
I don't think people can grow, either.
If you can't do your job with pride,
people won't accept you
in the first place.
They won't be able to like you.
Be someone people would want to see.
That's what you have to do.
It's not a question of wanting to have it.
If we don't have it...
I think it's over.
We can only do what we can right now.
November.
-Good morning.
Cold, isn't it? I think I'm going to die.
This is what the HiHi Jets trio are up to.
I got up at 3:30 a.m.
When you fall forwards...
Inoue is appearing in a movie.
And, action!
It came off!
-No, it wasn't us!
Cut!
No, it wasn't us!
It's not a big part,
but he throws himself into it.
Around the same time,
Takahashi is appearing in a TV drama.
DRAMA SERIAL W:
KARERA WO MIREBA WAKARU KOTO
I respected my father.
He was powerful.
A good communicator.
Takahashi's plan is to make
acting his weapon.
He's developed his skill
a little more again.
You don't need the script?
I don't have it on me much.
I memorize it before I start.
I master my lines at home.
That way, I'm not nervous here.
I make sure I practice enough
that I feel I can do it.
There's still a way to go
until the other two members return.
Until then, all they can do
is better themselves and wait.
Having the fans there for him
keeps Igari going.
All of the letters, more or less,
are kind words.
Sometimes people are harsh, too.
I suppose you remember
who your first fan was?
I do. Although it's more the first letter
that I remember, as opposed to the fan.
I remember that
it was in a light-blue envelope.
It's been three months
since the two members left.
Takahashi and Inoue
have resumed their roller skate lessons.
And, go.
Ouch!
Careful!
Keep going!
All right!
Almost!
Dammit!
That hurt...
Damn! I like it, that's the spirit.
DECEMBER 8, 2019
IMPERIAL THEATRE
Then December comes around.
Another new show has begun.
Okay, line up behind your number.
While other groups are performing
with all their members,
HiHi Jets are a trio.
Two members have withdrawn
from public life.
What feelings has this time
stirred in them?
As we keep evolving,
and we can all perform together again,
not only will those two level up,
but so will the whole group.
We'll be a higher-level group overall.
That's what I believe right now.
As I keep going.
Well, you know...
we'll be able to get along great.
I really feel that quite strongly.
In ten years' time,
even in several decades' time,
if the five of us can laugh
and have a good time together,
I think that will be enough for me.
And then, January.
The withdrawal period is over,
and they're once again operating
as a five-man group.
JANUARY 6, 2020
It's the 118th day since withdrawal began.
Good morning!
Thank you for allowing the five of us
to do our shoot today.
Thank you!
Sorry to disturb you.
Please excuse us.
For the first time in a long while,
the five are doing a photo shoot.
What they've lost won't come back easily.
They'll continue to be confronted
with the weight of the situation.
This is a path that they have chosen.
That was hilarious!
Again!
Sit.
Whoa!
That's because...
these five are HiHi Jets.
How was everyone? Really good.
They got really mad!
But...
I'm grateful for them getting mad.
I'm grateful they didn't give up on me.
As for Sakuma,
he took up the piano again in reclusion
after having given it up.
Apparently he was practicing
so he could be useful to the group.
I decided to dedicate my life
to the group,
and I haven't forgotten that.
I've decided to fully make
the group's dreams
my own dreams.
Over this period,
Takahashi was pursued continuously
by the same thought.
How did we do this
when there were five of us?
I started feeling that way
halfway through.
That scared me so much,
and there was nothing I could do.
So, having this feeling after so long
makes me happy.
That was funny, wasn't it?
Their dream is to be a legendary group.
The road to get there
is long and treacherous,
but they've set out on it once more.
On the next Ride On Time,
Kis-My-Ft2.
Cameras follow them
through a turbulent 180 days.
That was scary.
Everyone in Kis-My-Ft2
is getting to the 30 mark.
Never seen on the stage,
we see what reality is
for the seven of them.
If I thought about myself too much...
I'd fall apart.
And then...
TAIWAN
...they take to the world stage.
No matter where I am in the world,
I want to stand there
and show people what Kis-My is all about.
Subtitle translation by Lewis Williams