Look at this camera!
It's the end of 2019 and this group
is standing on their dream stage.
70TH NHK KOHAKU UTA GASSEN
REHEARSAL
This seven-member boy band
wearing roller skates
is Kis-My-Ft2.
Also known as "Kisumai."
It has taken them 15 years
to perform
on this singing competition show.
I was simply surprised.
I never saw it coming.
I couldn't believe it.
I can't believe I'll be performing there.
It doesn't even feel real to me yet.
We're not a typical Johnny's group
where every member
looks like Prince Charming.
We have a press conference.
Ouch!
-Ouch.
-You're such klutz.
I almost dislocated my shoulder.
You suck at multitasking.
They are neither typical nor princes.
They have blazed their own unique trail.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
-Guys, are you ready?
-Yes.
Kisumai claims
they are not a typical Johnny's group.
They have a genre
they've worked especially hard at.
Variety TV shows.
KISUMAI CHO BUSAIKU!? SET
Can you tell us
about your worst kiss ever?
Like, in detail?
Many people have learned the names
and faces of the seven members
while laughing along watching this show.
MAY 2019, TOKYO DOME
LIVE TOUR 2019 FREE HUGS!
Kisumai has a large presence
in the idol world.
Approximately 600,000 fans came
to their live tour in 2019.
That is the second highest after ARASHI
for a Johnny's group.
They have had 25 consecutive CDs
that have ranked number one
on the hit charts.
HIROMITSU KITAYAMA (34)
The eldest member who is like the leader
and is the group's MC,
Hiromitsu Kitayama.
I saw the King & Prince episodes.
They were so cool.
He has strong ideals
as to how this group should operate.
Yuta Tamamori is the front man of Kisumai.
YUTA TAMAMORI (29)
He has charming expressions
and a delicate air about him.
The man who is both cool and passionate
is Taisuke Fujigaya.
TAISUKE FUJIGAYA (32)
He brings sex appeal to the group.
BUSAIKU MURA NO WATTO! ODOROKU! DAIISSHO
Kisumai has one other unique feature.
Four of the seven members
form an in-group unit.
They are "Busaiku," meaning "ugly."
The three in the front row are handsome.
I'm not. I'm ugly.
I'm ugly and I know it.
Kento Senga is the youngest in the group.
KENTO SENGA (28)
He is a great dancer
and sometimes provides the choreography.
Walk here, then pose.
The member who's focused
on watching TV on his phone
is Wataru Yokoo.
He's watching our show.
He is?
He hasn't laughed once
since the show began.
He diligently watches his shows
to find room for improvement.
Yokoo has many strengths.
WATARU YOKOO (33)
On one TV show,
he shared haiku poems
that impressed even the professionals.
TAKASHI NIKAIDO (29)
Takashi Nikaido.
He's considerate of his junior members,
and even does his makeup
in their dressing room.
He takes such good care of us.
GENTA MATSUDA
-He's our big bro.
-That's right.
The younger members treat him
like their big brother.
Toshiya Miyata
is always the life of the party.
He is both cheerful
and considerate of others.
TOSHIYA MIYATA (31)
Please follow us around
everywhere we go from today.
-Thank you.
-No, thank you.
I hope I have enough gigs
for you to follow me too.
Oh! I will have a drama shoot
and a performance.
We follow the seven members
as they embark on separate journeys.
Ready? And, action!
It's December 2019,
and Tamamori is filming a drama.
You're still cooking lame food?
My lame food earned me a Michelin star.
He is playing the part of a young chef
working at a top-class hotel.
Tamamori started acting on TV shows
and in movies ten years ago.
We learn of his policy for acting
during a break between scenes.
He is holding a box of vegetables,
which are props.
Not yet. We're not filming yet.
It's fine. Let's do it.
Someone take this.
Don't make him carry such heavy props.
It's fine. I got them.
You'll tire yourself out.
You're going to regret this.
No. Let me hold them.
Props are crucial to acting.
Whether it be a bag of food you bought,
or the knife and frying pan you use.
They're props to create my character.
I don't want to be separated from them
for too long.
I hadn't given it much thought,
but I guess that's what it is.
His current approach
developed thanks to the hardships
that he experienced before his debut.
YUTA TAMAMORI
Kisumai was formed
as a Johnny's Jr. unit in 2005.
They waited for their CD debut,
but a younger group debuted ahead of them.
To be honest, I was bummed out
when Hey! Say! JUMP went ahead of us.
It struck me hard.
But it wasn't just me.
I'm sure that other members
felt the same way, too.
But that became our springboard.
It taught us not to sulk.
It fueled us to work harder.
It really lit our determination on fire.
That was the moment
when I felt both disappointed,
and determined never to give up
until it was our turn.
FEB. 12, 2011
KIS-MY-FT NI AERU DE SHOW VOL.3
At a concert nine years ago...
For real?
Did you two know about this?
What is it?
-What? No way!
-You're kidding?
Is this for real?
Their CD debut came out of the blue.
-Yes!
-Seriously?
Yes!
Kitayama became an idol
in the most unexpected way.
JOHNNY'S JUNIOR DAYS
HIROMITSU KITAYAMA
His dream was to become
a professional soccer player.
But when he entered high school,
he happened to meet Tomohisa Yamashita,
who was already an idol.
TOMOHISA YAMASHITA
Kitayama became interested in being idol
and decided to give it a shot.
Fearless curiosity
has always been his driving force.
It's better to have tried than not.
I want to know
that I've at least given it a shot.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be able to stand it.
In the autumn of 2019,
Kitayama was taking on a new challenge...
The stage play, THE NETHER.
MITSURU HIRATA
He plays a detective
who investigates crimes in virtual space.
BAIJAKU NAKAMURA
Kitayama is always the first to arrive
at rehearsals.
Iris. Henrietta.
You had a taste
for girls of the same look.
Good morning, sir.
I have something I must accomplish
in the Nether.
Many people are connected to me.
You cannot exile me from the Nether.
You seem to have a taste for antiques.
You will simply be returning
to the time they come from.
This is a violation of human rights!
DIRECTOR
MISAKI SETOYAMA
Kitayama's line delivery
became the subject of debate.
This line.
"You create one girl after the other.
Just like the girl before."
The intonation of this line sounds wrong.
Where should the stress go?
I think you're doing it wrong.
"The girl before"?
Both are grammatically correct.
The way you're saying it now,
it's the girl in front of you.
In front?
If you mean "from before,"
it's the latter intonation.
Just like the girl before.
You create one girl after the other.
Yes. That sounds clearer.
You and your family...
There is a creed that Kitayama holds
when he is working alone
and away from the group.
I'll have them take care of it.
I wouldn't get individual gigs
if it weren't for Kisumai.
So in the end, it's all for the group.
It's the same for all of us.
If we become selfish,
the group will fall apart.
I can be on TV and in movies
because I'm a part of Kisumai.
We're a bunch of ordinary guys.
We tried to figure out
how we could become popular.
Then we had a CD debut.
Then, we did a show at Tokyo Dome.
We even have our own TV show.
How cool is that?
Fujigaya also has an acting gig
in December 2019.
He plays the part of a young man
who has dedicated his life to carpentry.
It requires great focus to use the plane.
Action!
Cut! Let's check the scene.
Thank you.
-It's so difficult.
-Yeah.
But I think I'm getting the hang of it.
It felt good in the end, didn't it?
It feels good because you nail it
when the camera rolls.
I can tell you nailed it.
-That was awesome.
-Really?
I have a wonderful teacher.
I somehow managed.
I'm not good with my hands.
It's so difficult.
It takes a lot of practice.
In this profession,
you rarely get praised.
I was really flattered.
TAISUKE FUJIGAYA
Fujigaya joined Johnny's
when he was 11 years old.
He always sought the praise
of a certain man.
He was Fujigaya's mentor
and father-figure.
That man loved musicals.
REHEARSAL FOR MUSICAL DON JUAN
Then in 2019,
Fujigaya was able to star in a musical.
It is the story of a lady's man
who finds true love.
Fujigaya was playing the lead role.
We don't have a mark for you.
-Are you okay with that?
-Yes.
You can just rush in and rush out.
How does the choreography go after this?
The story is set in Spain.
Fujigaya must learn to dance the flamenco.
What's the most difficult part?
What? Everything.
This is all new to me.
It's tough.
Food is his escape
between demanding rehearsals.
I really want fried chicken.
However, Fujigaya must
lose weight for the role,
so he can only eat salad.
Fujigaya has had difficulty singing
as a musical actor.
Singing in English goes like this.
Light. "T."
It often ends with a consonant.
You want the energy of the word
to travel during this space.
It makes the music more sentimental.
-I see what you mean.
-You need to punctuate it.
This is tough.
This is what you're missing here.
You have gotten better at it today.
Enunciate the entire word.
Use the entire word to express yourself.
This is Fujigaya's first musical.
How will he deliver the role?
Fujigaya from Kisumai is starring in
a musical for the first time... Don Juan.
It is moments before the curtain rises.
You don't need to.
Fujigaya asks us
to stop the camera for the first time.
Then...
Yes!
DON JUAN MUSICAL
During the curtain call on the final show,
Fujigaya speaks to the audience
about his gratitude toward
that certain man.
I'm from Johnny's.
Mr. Johnny really loved musicals.
He passed away
while I was still rehearsing.
I was at a loss when he was gone.
Mr. Johnny always told us,
"Show must go on."
Those words helped me complete
these 30 nights playing Don Juan.
Fujigaya had been fighting great pressure.
It made him a man of few words,
even with our cameras rolling,
but Fujigaya finally opens up.
I was scared.
But I had faith.
I knew Mr. Johnny was watching over me,
which is why I trudged through.
I'm glad I didn't run from this challenge.
I'm so glad I met this company of actors.
I couldn't be happier.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
On the next Ride on Time,
we follow Busaiku.
We must prove what we can accomplish
when it's just us four.
We are being put to the test.
We need to be intelligent,
or soon we will have no gigs.
We follow them backstage
as they prepare for their show.
This is hard.
We hang out with junior members,
and meet a mentor who has supported them
through the years.
I've...
I've felt so much love for us from him.
Subtitle translation by Natsuka Koshimi