Wait, I didn't have my mic on.
-You have five minutes.
-Okay.
It happened during the rehearsal.
That day came suddenly.
As he was singing a song,
Hirano suddenly began to cry.
What was the reason behind those tears?
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
Another stage play is
about to be born in this studio.
The ones to take center stage
are King & Prince.
The three members
who went by the name Mr. King
before they debuted.
Can we try from the start?
KAITO TAKAHASHI (20)
For these three, who are actively
appearing in movies, dramas, and TV shows,
this stage play is an opportunity
to re-evaluate themselves.
SHO HIRANO (22)
Look at it.
There's so much to do.
We have to sing, dance,
and act.
It is called JOHNNYS' IsLAND.
Their father-figure in this business
integrated all aspects
of entertainment into
this epic culmination of a stage play.
Not only that,
these three were left
with a massive assignment.
When he was alive,
he cherished these words
more than anything.
To stand on stage
no matter what happens.
"The real meaning behind these words..."
The theme of this stage play
is to reconsider
the meaning behind these words.
-Mr. Johnny liked this spot?
-Yeah.
He'd watch rehearsals here.
Are you off-center? Are you okay?
This is better.
What thoughts were imbued in those words?
November, 2019.
The opening day is just a month away
and rehearsals are in full swing.
Their first hurdle is the taiko drums.
This will...
-delay one at a time.
-Okay.
They must hit the drums
at slightly different times.
It requires a technique
completely different
from regular drumming.
This is bad.
Actually, these taiko drums
are a fusion of Japanese
and western styles,
and they must play along to
electronic music.
-Can I listen to that again?
-I am completely lost.
It's the hardest thing I've done so far.
Because we're playing to digital sounds.
They only have a few days
to practice the taiko.
They are all determined.
Oh, no. My head is spinning.
Sorry!
One more time. From the start, please.
Can we try from the same place?
One, two, three, four.
Repeating it over and over again.
That is Nagase's method.
Everyone goes to sleep and wakes up
with the routine still memorized.
But I forget everything.
I have to repeat it, or I can't remember.
That's normal, though.
I'm just working on what I can't do.
Okay, let's do it.
Today, Hirano is practicing the flying
routine, which he's done before.
He hangs inside a sphere
and completes the moves.
He is trying to grasp the feeling
of spinning in the air
as if he were swimming.
That's rough first thing in the morning.
Your inner ears readjust.
Do they adjust in the first place?
They do.
They really do.
By the final performance,
you don't even get dizzy anymore.
If the audience sees this
and is impressed by it,
that will make me happy.
Meanwhile, Takahashi...
is working on an important scene.
What is the most important part?
Mr. Johnny spent a week
on these four lines.
-Seriously?
-Without changing it...
He is earnestly contemplating
one word written in the script.
"War."
-Big brother!
-It's an incendiary bomb!
A fundamental part of this theater
is a scene that portrays war.
I don't want them to experience
this tragedy!
As someone who lived through the war,
he purposely had these youths,
who are aspiring to become idols,
face the tragic realities of life.
Because that history is forgotten now,
he wants you to remember it and realize
your happiness is a product
of those hard times.
To not take it for granted.
Throw it whichever way you're facing.
As if you are throwing down
a bomb or grenade.
Boom, boom, boom.
The scene leading up to that line
depicts the brutality of war.
Use your hands in your own way,
to show that you're in pain
and writhing.
He will portray that with dance.
Takahashi has given himself
a difficult task.
It's not a school club.
This is my career and my livelihood,
so I feel a responsibility
to stand on stage.
It's our job to bring joy to people,
so I do think of it as my mission.
For Takahashi,
that is what "show must go on"
means to him now.
Amidst practice,
the five of them come together.
Very good.
Welcome!
They're reliable teammates
who each have areas they excel in.
Hirano was still struggling with the taiko
and asked Kishi...
The taiko is so fast this time.
Really?
Hey, Kishi.
Is there a word that fits in this rhythm?
Mammoth exhibition.
Mammoth exhibition?
Mammoth exhibition,
mammoth exhibition, okay, okay.
MAMMOTH EXHIBITION
It's hard to say.
Kishi and Jinguji,
who were asked for advice,
also faced that theme
left by their dear friend
through theater last year.
A story about youths
finding the meaning of life
through boxing.
There are things they know
now that they've done it.
I was able to experience
the joy of theater all over again.
"Tomorrow is better than yesterday,"
is how I feel.
Our goal was to give a good performance,
so once it was done,
I felt glad that I worked hard,
and it was so much fun.
Everything comes back to you like that.
-Hello.
Nice to meet you.
They have one week until opening day.
The three of them must learn
a difficult dance routine.
Since it's the three of you,
we have three people as well.
The song they'll be dancing to
is called "Chanbara."
Boom. Then, repeat it. One, two, three...
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Then spin around.
Nagase is having some trouble.
Fifteen minutes into it...
-Can we do one-on-one?
-Yeah.
-Not as a group. Can you teach me?
-Sure.
Slowly but surely.
He makes sure each step is correct
and memorizes the moves.
Five, six...
And 30 minutes later.
Let's slowly do it together.
The three of you.
Ren, if you turn a little more this way...
I see. I'm going straight.
I'm coming up from the back,
so I almost bump into you.
-Okay.
-Sorry.
When you move positions,
make your movements bigger.
Diagonally? Sorry about that.
Ready...
No matter how hard it is,
they must find the answers on their own
and create something new.
I think Mr. Johnny
purposely didn't explain
what "show must go on" meant.
He'd say, "show must go on,"
but he wouldn't go into detail.
We have to find the meaning ourselves
and make our own decisions.
As long as we have an audience,
we have to continue.
Nagase continues to search
for the meaning of those words.
IMPERIAL THEATRE
It is opening day.
Rehearsals start in the afternoon
and showtime is at night.
Until then, they go through
and inspect each item
on their long checklist
and make their own decisions.
The part that goes, "I can bet my life"
is the only time.
-That's one, right?
-That's one.
It's one.
Actually, this stage play
has a part that was kept a secret
even during rehearsals.
The starring members will speak
about their memories of him.
KEEPSAKES ON STAGE
There is no set script.
They will express their real feelings.
OPEN REHEARSAL
That scene was performed
during the open rehearsal.
Look, you guys!
A poster of the show
he attended until he passed.
I was so nervous that day!
When I see the scratches on it,
it reminds me...
Items they've practiced with
all this time...
Those memorable items fill up the stage.
...he talked to me.
I gave him this vest for his birthday.
HIDAKA UKISHO
He wore it every day,
and that made me so happy.
The first time he heard me sing,
he said it was basic.
But he said I should try enka,
and when I did, he praised me so much.
TAISHO IWASAKI
I was so happy.
Their feelings for him flow forth.
This was triggered by...
Hirano's performance of
the song expressing
a sense of emptiness
after losing someone dear.
That day came suddenly.
When it slips out of my hands
I realize for the first time
The importance of what I lost
When it disappears from my heart
I realize I am lonely
The curtains will rise for opening day.
Welcome to the dream stage,
JOHNNYS' IsLAND.
It's the first time doing this show
since his death.
The Japanese taiko and electronic fusion
the three of them worked hard to create.
And "Chanbara,"
the dance Nagase had difficulties with.
My favorite one out of
all of them is "Chanbara."
When I saw the dance for the first time,
I thought it was insanely difficult.
But once I tried it and memorized it,
it was so fun to do.
Like real dancing.
The war scene, which Takahashi himself
choreographed and contemplated
to portray the script.
Throughout history,
humans are always fighting.
This ordinary life is a blessing.
We need to...
count our blessings.
-Hello.
These two have come to watch the show.
It feels strange to watch
JOHNNYS' IsLAND so objectively.
Oh, no.
I'm super excited.
Last year, Kishi and Jinguji
stood on the same stage.
How will it look to them?
-That's amazing.
-It looks so real.
What caught them by surprise
was the scene where they talk about
their fond memories of him.
I don't really remember.
Back then...
Takahashi knew the two of them
were watching.
He began to talk about
how their group formed their bond.
He said, "You are going to be
Mr. King vs Mr. Prince from today."
It was our first group.
It gave us so much hope.
A lot happened,
and we separated for a bit,
but the next time we came together
was when we debuted.
To think that he believed in us
that whole time makes me happy.
Let's work hard from now on.
Yeah.
Let's work hard.
They did not expect to witness
something like this.
-...three of us.
-Everyone on Earth
was clapping right now.
And the finale.
Overwhelmed with emotions,
the two of them run to the stage.
Thank you! Have a safe trip home.
-How was it?
-I was so moved.
What moved you?
Your soul.
Everyone's soul.
I got goosebumps so many times.
-You did? Really?
-I did.
After seeing the stage play,
what is their take on "show must go on,"
a phrase taught
by the person so dear to them?
Making people happy,
not creating negativity, and staying
positive no matter what happens
is what "show must go on" means.
In the future, for example...
there will always be
ups and downs in life,
but we have to charge forward
toward our dream,
and bring more happiness to people,
and ultimately just keep living life.
I think that phrase is a way of living.
And then it was New Year's Eve.
JOHNNY'S COUNTDOWN 2019-2020
They were faced with
a "show must go on" moment.
70TH NHK KOHAKU UTA GASSEN
It's the second New Year's Eve
since King & Prince was born.
We talked about
changing it up for Kohaku. When Kaito
sings it, he sounds like Sukima Switch.
-He's going to mess up on stage.
-I know.
-We're ready.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
They don't seem nervous
as they walk onto a prestigious stage.
King & Prince blasts through
their second year.
They continue to
push themselves to their limit.
They know the importance of honest,
steady work.
The audience here can't see very well.
They look for new skills.
I can't think at all.
Good evening! I'm...
They work to widen their boundaries.
Is that not allowed by my agency?
Radio is interesting, though.
They make an earnest effort
to live as idols.
They will continue on this journey.
Doing the shows are a sign
of peace, and we can do the shows
because there is peace.
That's what I think.
And so, the "show must go on" in a sense
and we can't let that end.
Ready...
We have a mission!
CM SHOOTING
-Start.
-This is the best Puccho!
The one with gummies!
-Obviously, the balls are way better.
-Crunchy outside, soft inside!
Cut!
We're all heading toward the same goal
and working hard.
-We're trying to be serious.
-We're talking about our dreams.
How will they edit this?
-It'll get cut out, don't worry.
-I want them to use that.
On the next Ride on Time...
STARTING FROM TOKYO DOME
A five-member unit
working toward their debut...
HiHi Jets.
A documentary spanning eight months.
We follow them as they work hard
while experiencing setbacks and growth.
You almost had it.
But they are faced with a huge trial.
You have to come back. To the five of us.
I mean, three of us.
Each of us must become
someone who is needed,
so that we become needed
as a group as well.
That's the most important thing.
The latent strength
of these youths will be tested.
Subtitle translation by Kiko Morita