JANUARY 6, 2020
A group of five are together
for the first time in four months.
Good morning!
Thank you for allowing the five of us
to do our shoot today.
Thank you!
Sorry to disturb you.
Please excuse us.
Thank you.
It's the idol unit HiHi Jets.
Today's the all-important
calendar photo shoot.
But there's a heavy mood,
and nobody wants to talk.
It's due to an incident
that two of the members caused.
HIHI JETS' BLOG
It stopped the group in its tracks.
FOUR-MONTH WITHDRAWAL FROM ACTIVITY
It won't happen again.
Because if it does, it's the end.
Our dreams are at stake,
as are three of our lives.
RYUTO SAKUMA
I didn't think I was too bothered...
RYO HASHIMOTO
...by how I was perceived,
but I was so afraid.
I can't sleep at night.
Smile!
There's somewhere they can't hope to go
if there aren't all five of them.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
This year will be the fifth
since HiHi Jets formed.
Their weapon is the roller skate,
a Johnny's tradition.
Four of the members are in their teens,
with two of them being in high school.
Us in HiHi Jets...
They have a cheeky side, too.
People who shout out to us, HiHi Jets,
will get top priority for fan service!
-HiHi!
We're always raising our ambitions
higher and higher.
If we set a limit,
we wouldn't grow beyond it.
So, we don't set limits.
-One big cheer.
-Is "Yeah!" okay?
They always have a team talk before gigs.
Let's do this!
-All right.
-Okay.
Quite anticlimactic.
That's how we do team talks.
We are HiHi Jets.
And their dream is...
To become a legendary group.
I think the five of us can do it.
We first join them in June.
-Okay, shall we put the skates on?
-Yes.
Rehearsals have begun
for their summer shows.
Let's do it.
Their roller-skating routine
demands a good sense of balance.
The members are tremendously athletic.
Soya Igari is the youngest.
SOYA IGARI (17)
He choreographs the skating routines.
Four is one-and-a-half beats.
He was scouted by the agency
eight years ago
when they spotted his talent.
A lot is demanded of him.
Hey, don't mess around. Stop.
That was all wrong. Don't goof around.
I didn't make it in time.
The oldest and the group's center,
Yuto Takahashi, isn't spared.
YUTO TAKAHASHI (20)
Oh, it's this way!
Takahashi was the latest of the five
to join the agency.
He's also an inexperienced skater.
-You okay?
-Are you all right?
He was devoted to baseball
through middle school.
After graduating,
he dived into this world.
SIGNS WITH JOHNNY'S AT AGE 15
I was a catcher.
-Were you?
-Yes.
Which raises the question...
If HiHi was a baseball team,
-what positions would everyone play?
-What positions?
Who would be the pitcher?
Oh, let me think.
I'm curious to hear this.
Igari would be the pitcher.
RYUTO SAKUMA (17)
What about Ryuto Sakuma,
who is the joint-youngest with Igari?
Maybe the shortstop.
-He's extremely observant.
-Oh?
See? He noticed that.
He can play the piano, he can skate...
RYO HASHIMOTO (19)     MIZUKI INOUE (19)
And what of Ryo Hashimoto
and Mizuki Inoue,
who have been with the agency
for ten years?
Hashimoto would be...
on third base.
He could even do third base fourth.
He's talking about me.
He's a big, solid guy.
Ryo Hashimoto's a proper man.
Second base would be Mizuki.
The second baseman is very important.
-Yeah, yeah.
-The man on second...
Once he gets onto baseball,
he doesn't stop.
You should see Kikuchi play.
Hey! I said we were doing it!
-I want to be like Ichiro.
-Come on!
-Never mind.
-Sorry!
-I'll do it.
-I'm sorry!
We're getting nowhere like this.
Their ages may differ,
but there's no seniority in the group.
Tidying up the roller skates today
is one of the eldest, Hashimoto.
Thank you.
As long as you're not rude
to the person you're talking to,
you can talk to any other member
like you're on the same level.
Yeah. You don't want to be taken lightly.
We tell each other how we really feel.
In charge of tying everyone together
is the group's center, Takahashi.
All right!
Today, Takahashi is appearing
alongside members from rival groups
on a TV variety show.
They have to remake a table
owned by a member of the public
into a foldable one.
All right, let's get straight to it!
Let's do it!
This and the outside...
As a professional instructs them,
they take the table apart and rebuild it.
After six hours of work, it's ready.
A screw's sticking out.
-On the top.
-Oh, man...
They've damaged the precious table.
There's a problem with the legs, too.
At the very end,
this just isn't satisfactory.
It's jutting out.
We've done something inexcusable.
I'm very sorry, but we're going
to have to give this back.
-Okay, and move.
-Take it that way.
Right.
After the recording,
Takahashi goes to apologize
to the table's owner of his own volition.
Here's what he said when asked why.
That's how my parents brought...
No, how they are bringing me up.
You can't forget to be grateful.
They've always told me that.
You see us guys on the screen,
but there are people other than us,
lots of people,
who are working with us from the morning.
And it's thanks to them
we're able to do this,
but I've been a nuisance
to all of those people.
Maybe not a nuisance,
but I feel like
I've made a problem for them,
and that feels horrible.
No matter what it's about.
It's this attitude which is why
he is in the group's center.
Thank you so much.
Thank you. See you again soon.
The summer performances are drawing near.
They need to decide
which songs they'll perform.
-Shall we make it flashy?
-We'd better not.
Maybe rock-type songs,
and we can wear suits?
Not suits.
Maybe something stylish, then.
Something scary. Like gang-style outfits.
Something you don't see from Johnny's.
You don't see that,
which is why we have to do it now.
We need to decide.
Clashing their ideas against each other's
is their method.
HIHI JETS EX THEATER
This is the resulting finished set list.
The 90-minute show features an astounding
26 songs, including the encore.
It's seriously long.
We feel like, "I just want
to show you this," about everything.
It'd be a shame to drop any of it.
-They're all highlights.
-Yeah.
I like all of them.
They decide to do them all in the end.
We all speak our minds,
so it's hard to reach a decision.
We want to all be equal.
Being with people
who have differing opinions
means you hear new,
interesting perspectives.
"Great idea," you think.
JULY 24, 2019
It's the rehearsal
ten days before the show.
The five will be taking this on.
It's a 1,7-meter-tall roller-skating ramp.
They'll be speeding down it
towards the audience.
I am a bit scared. It's huge.
Here goes.
Igari goes first.
It's a breeze for him.
-Go ahead.
-Okay.
The same for the agile Sakuma.
With room to spare!
-You didn't use the brakes?
-No.
After Inoue and Hashimoto also succeed,
it's Takahashi's turn last.
-Here I go!
-Okay!
Ouch...
It's because you're scared.
Take a breather.
If he can't do it,
they'll have to consider a change of plan.
The protective gear does nothing!
If you have your right foot on it,
step out with your left.
You don't want to move this.
And balance on it.
Balance on that, and as your left foot
steps out, shift your weight forward.
This is the only day that's been assigned
to ramp practice.
He removes his helmet to finally do it
like he will for the real thing.
This is scary.
You all went as you turned, right?
Just in case,
the crew block him from falling
off the stage.
-I really might crash into you.
-Which way will you go?
-This way.
-Okay.
Look out!
You smashed right into them!
Oh no!
Every mat...
You touched every single mat!
Even at times like this,
no kind words are offered.
You should choose one way.
I think you can do it, though.
Start turning where you want to go
from the offset.
Remember to turn from the start.
-Here goes.
-Okay.
-All right! Perfect. All done.
-Mission cleared!
We can do "One Kiss" now.
Oh, boy.
I'm glad I managed to do it.
It's seriously tall, though.
Takahashi went through
a trying period in his life.
PHOTO COURTESY OF WINK UP
When the group first formed,
despite having no dancing
or skating experience,
he was entrusted with being
the group's center.
Unable to keep up in rehearsals,
it once seemed like
the pressure was too much.
Being part of the group
meant I was suffering.
There was so much.
Thinking about it now...
I wasn't putting in nearly enough effort.
Thinking about it now,
I wonder how tough it really was.
It really wasn't that bad.
This was Inoue's response
when asked about that time.
He was hopeless,
so I really disliked him back then.
Wow, he really sucked.
But he can do it all now.
That's why I think he's brilliant.
He's not a kid who whines
that he can't do something.
Not a kid, a guy.
He's a guy who keeps going
until he can do it.
It's this approach
that's taken Takahashi all this way.
If I was to give it all up today...
Well, maybe it did happen once.
To decide I wasn't capable of improving...
was something I refused to do, though,
because something in the back of my head
stopped me.
I couldn't leave it behind.
-It could be information overload.
-Overload?
The five have always clashed
with each other honestly.
And that's precisely why
their bonds are so solid.
That's so true!
We know ourselves better than anyone.
We'd never do that.
AUGUST 3-23, 2019
And then the stage curtain lifts.
PAPA MAMA ICHIBAN
HADAKA NO SHONEN NATSU MATSURI!
Can you make some noise?
Yeah!
They use the ramp for more than
just the opening,
racing through tight gaps.
To expand the group's repertoire
even further, Hashimoto plays guitar.
And Igari raps his own lyrics
to music he wrote.
Thank you very much!
The end!
Done!
Next, it's the biggest Johnny's Jr. show,
the Tokyo Dome Concert.
However, something is weighing
on their minds.
JULY 24, 2019
It's something that happened
a few days ago in rehearsals.
Ouch!
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
-Thanks.
-Got it.
After a thumb injury,
they await the day with some trepidation.
AUGUST 7, 2019
August.
Around 300 Johnny's Jr. idols
will be performing here tomorrow
for the Tokyo Dome Concert.
It's so... It's so big.
The focal point f HiHi Jets is,
of course, roller-skating.
It's a great opportunity for them to show
what they've got to 55,000 people.
However, Igari's done it again.
It hurts. Damn.
I've really messed it up. I can't turn it.
-It's my wrist.
-Your wrist?
The left one again.
It's an injury that will affect
every aspect of the performance.
-How did you do it?
-On the ramp.
That's because Igari was assigned the task
of using his roller skates
to jump over nine people.
They won't let him risk further injury.
Brought in as a last-minute replacement
is the nimble Sakuma.
I'll do my best.
It's the group's greatest chance
to make their mark.
Failure isn't an option.
Here I come!
Is he here?
He gets it on the first attempt.
It's down to the strength they've fostered
by always making each other tougher.
Whoa! Awesome!
Saku-chan really is an amazing guy.
He can do anything.
Seriously, I mean...
With a relieved look on his face,
Igari recalls a bitter experience.
Two years ago,
because of an injury he had suffered,
none of the members could appear
on a TV music show they aspired to be on
and their opportunities were reduced.
If I were in their shoes,
I'd have wanted me
to take responsibility.
It was a really big deal.
For Johnny's Jr. artists, Music Station
is a major platform. It's big.
You really want to get your foot
in that door,
so being booked to be on it
was an incredible chance.
Us losing that opportunity...
was something
I couldn't apologize enough for.
But it was because of that
that I changed my outlook on things.
I wanted to be more grateful
for my band mates.
I realized how lucky I was.
My sense of gratitude
for being able to do this
while surrounded by such great people
became stronger.
AUGUST 8, 2019
Time for the real thing.
Hello! We're HiHi Jets!
Tokyo Dome!
And they reach the peak
of their performance.
Here we go!
Go!
-Here he comes!
-All right!
Cheer him on!
Oh no!
Very cool!
This group that hopes to achieve
legendary status
has taken one step closer to that dream.
All done.
That was fun.
It was fun. All new stuff.
However, after this
they will be met with a big setback.
A lot happened.
Next, on Ride On Time...
HiHi Jets face a crisis.
What scares me most
is that the two of them
might not come back.
Two members are hit by a scandal.
WITHDRAWAL FROM ACTIVITY
The five are suddenly separated.
What will become of their dream
of being a legendary group?
I had to consider what I'd do
if the group couldn't go on anymore.
In case it went south.
A relationship of trust.
If we can't have that,
I don't think us five can stay together.
Where will fate lead them?
We can only do what we can right now.
Subtitle translation by Lewis Williams