This is a group with a strength
that's unlike any other idols.
The tour went by in the blink of an eye.
Today is the last show.
-Right? How sad.
-I know.
-Did you put your nose on already?
-Yeah, I did.
I see.
It's always on my face!
Ha!
We're already making fools of ourselves
on Ride On Time.
-Sorry.
-Sorry about that.
-We're dumb.
-Sorry.
This is our appeal.
Where are we going?
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
MAY 2019, TOKYO DOME
LIVE TOUR 2019 FREE HUGS!
The seven-member boy band,
Kis-My-Ft2, is also known as Kisumai.
Over 600,000 fans came
to their five-dome tour in 2019.
Since their debut,
they have had 25 consecutive CDs that
have ranked number one on the hit charts.
What do the members think
their group's appeal is?
I think it's how we're not very idol-like.
That's definitely our strength, I'm sure.
We even have an in-group unit
called "Busaiku."
BUSAIKU MURA NO WATTO! ODOROKU! DAIISSHO
Four members make up Busaiku.
BUSAIKU
Busaiku means "ugly".
They have cleared a path for themselves
with comical performances.
The three in the front row are handsome.
I'm not. I'm ugly.
I'm ugly and I know it.
KENTO SENGA (28)
Here are the members.
Kento Senga, the youngest.
He is a great dancer
and sometimes provides the choreography.
We walk up to here, then duck.
That's what we do now.
You seem to have matured.
How old are you now?
Thirty-three.
Seriously? You are?
Wataru Yokoo is popular on variety shows.
WATARU YOKOO (33)
On one TV show,
he shared haiku poems
that impressed even the professionals.
We ask him for tips.
I'll be honest. You have to study for it.
He's filming us.
Takashi Nikaido spends whatever time
he has with his junior Johnny's members.
He takes such good care of us.
GENTA MATSUDA
-He's our big bro.
-That's right.
KISUMAI CHO BUSAIKU!? READING
Toshiya Miyata
is always the life of the party.
TOSHIYA MIYATA (31)
-Throw it in?
-Yes, please.
I'll throw it in. I'm a great MC.
Then I need to do my best to stop him.
The members of Busaiku
share a common goal.
Tamamori, Kitayama and Fujigaya
are all very important to us.
They carry so much of the load
for the seven of us.
We must prove what we can accomplish
when it's just us four.
We are being put to the test.
Their challenge has begun.
POSTER PHOTO SHOOT
MARUMARU NA HITO NO MATSURO
Busaiku will be performing a stage play.
It has a very unique structure.
They are breaking up into two teams,
Yokoo with Senga
and Miyata with Nikaido.
Each pair will play the same two brothers.
The story unfolds in a desolate town
out in the suburbs.
So, you'll be right up near this window.
Their characters have traits
that will be a challenge to act.
You will look
to the house across the street.
Take it all in.
Feel the weather.
OLDER BROTHER: MIYATA
YOUNGER BROTHER: NIKAIDO
Yokoo and Miyata are playing
the elder brother, who is blind.
Senga and Nikaido are playing
the younger brother who takes care of him.
They can do that using dictation software.
Miyata has the most acting experience
of the Busaiku members.
However, he has never played
the role of a blind man.
I don't want you
to try and help him as his eyes.
Guess what?
Yesterday, they asked me
if I wanted to work full-time.
-They did?
-Yeah.
But I don't know.
Miyata must convince the audience
that he is really blind.
That's good news.
Maybe you look this way
when you're talking.
-Oh, I get it.
-Right?
When you're happy,
you might react with your body.
Then it seems like you're reacting
to what's going on here.
How will he get into character?
Don't let our eyes meet...
This is difficult.
-It is.
-So hard.
"Really?" I can't look at you like this.
You're totally looking this way.
But I know you're in this direction.
He can still tell which direction
the voice is coming from.
But if I turn towards your voice,
it looks like we are looking eye to eye
as we talk.
I can't stop myself
from relying on my eyes.
To not be able to see...
This is tough.
-Don't you think?
-Totally.
-It created a buzz, didn't it?
-It did.
It's a beautiful day out.
How are Yokoo and Senga doing?
OLDER BROTHER: YOKOO
YOUNGER BROTHER: SENGA
Yokoo is playing the complex role
of the blind man
who's hobby is taking photos.
That sounds about right.
I've already been blind half my life.
How time flies.
What about the photos?
How will I take them?
From up here or down here?
There are many blind photographers.
Like I wrote in the script,
they rely on other senses
like smell and the feeling in the air.
Many blind photographers
exist around the world.
But would they take photos like this?
Or down here?
-It depends?
-I guess so.
It depends on the individual.
I'll do some research into that myself.
You're right.
There's no need to hold the camera up.
Yokoo likes to research thoroughly
before getting started.
It is lunch break between rehearsals.
He's watching our show.
He is?
He loves it.
He loves Kisumai.
We only have a 45-minute break.
Yet, he doesn't eat or rest.
He uses it to watch us on a variety show.
Unbelievable.
He hasn't laughed once
since the show began.
He hasn't?
Yokoo uses all his time
to think about Kisumai.
What is an idol anyway?
I think about it these days.
Snow Man and SixTONES will have a CD debut
in January 2020.
There are many younger members
beneath them.
Kisumai are approaching their thirties.
That means we need to find our niche.
We need to think and figure that out,
or else we will no longer have gigs.
Right now, we're just riding along a path
that our seniors laid out for us.
I want to create something and pass it on
to those who come after us,
as a group or as individuals.
BUSAIKU
The four members have been able to form
Busaiku and rise to acclaim
because of the support their seniors
have given them.
BUSAIKU MURA NO WATTO! ODOROKU! DAIISSHO
A surprise guest appeared
on the first Busaiku live tour.
It was Masahiro Nakai.
It was Nakai
who produced and named Busaiku.
How does this look?
How is the gap between songs?
There's a light here. Oh, it turned on.
What you see on stage is totally different
from the audience.
At least one member should observe
from off-stage before the real show.
Maybe you're one-seventh of a group
when performing as Kisumai,
but you're not each just one quarter
of Busaiku.
You are each one whole.
You need to each carry your load,
or this will flop.
-Remember that.
-Yes.
-Give it all you got.
-Yes, sir.
If you mess up, I'm going to bust you up.
-We'll do you proud.
These words from Nakai
helped the four members
find confidence in themselves.
TOSHIYA MIYATA (31)
I'm mature now.
Before,
I thought I was just a member of a group.
Now I see myself as an individual.
Since then,
my attitude has changed completely.
I think it has.
So, wherever I go, I am me.
Hi.
Nikaido follows Nakai's example
and takes care of the younger members.
Today, he has found free time to watch
a performance by the younger members.
TRAVIS JAPAN
TRAJYA NINJAPAN
Travis Japan is a Johnny's Jr. unit
renowned for all its members
having superb dance technique.
The unit is seven years old,
and they are waiting for their CD debut.
Nikaido knows what that feels like.
You messed up on the trampoline.
-He sucks.
-Yep. This guy sucks.
You cracked me up.
Oh, hey!
Only you messed up.
I was too nervous.
-What's up?
-He messed up the trampoline.
You were like this on the ground.
I fell and went down on my knees.
Oh, shoot.
You're always here when we mess up.
That was so uncool.
That's harsh. You're so harsh.
Unbelievable.
Nikaido rejoices in the success
of the younger members like it is his own.
You were so wobbly.
So many criticisms. I can't handle it.
But you did well. It was amazing.
Thank you.
Nakai has had a big influence on me.
He took good care of Kisumai.
He's always been so caring
towards Busaiku, too.
I've felt so much love for us from him.
Nakai has been a huge influence on me.
I care about them a lot.
The play's set is ready.
Their preparation is reaching its climax.
Miyata is playing a blind man.
How will he capture not only the movements
of the character but also his mind?
Sorry! I took too long to get ready.
In this scene,
Hisashi leaves the house first but stops.
Toshiyuki understands many things
just from this action.
Hisashi? What's the matter?
So, he comes...
Though they are in a hurry,
he doesn't hear footsteps.
Hisashi?
What's the matter?
You're getting the hang of it.
Yeah, I get it.
-I get it.
-Now I see.
It's not a scene between the three
from the beginning. It just you two.
-See.
-I misunderstood.
Everything is done by trial and error.
Miyata is usually cheerful.
However, recently,
he has become a man of few words.
There are only a few more days left
of rehearsals.
Busaiku is starring in a play
for the first time.
Yokoo is playing a blind man,
and Senga is playing his younger brother.
Time is running out.
-Hey there!
-Hi.
You sounded like a woman.
Yokoo does not seem to be anxious.
He carries out the rehearsals diligently.
They live upstairs...
However, he is still trying to figure out
how to use the camera.
I need to remember that later I will carry
both the camera and a white cane.
That's right.
Okay. I'll keep that in mind.
Senga is having a difficult time
figuring out his role.
Yes. You want to see him off.
You need a girlfriend!
This is the scene he is stuck on.
-I'm not popular with girls.
-What?
No way.
You lie!
You deserve a good girl.
-He does.
-Yeah.
He's had it rough, living alone
with his brother since he turned 17.
A person like me
doesn't deserve happiness.
Don't be stupid.
I don't deserve to be happy, ever.
"A person like me
doesn't deserve happiness."
Senga is unsure how to deliver this line.
Yeah, totally.
I...
I don't deserve it.
The brothers have a complicated past.
Senga has yet to figure out
how to express it in his acting.
That's how Mom died.
I have quite a few things to work out.
You mean emotional matters?
Yes, I can't decide yet.
How should I portray the younger brother?
Is it better if I play Hisashi
as more innocently juvenile?
Or is it better...
if I play him more neutrally?
In my opinion...
Senga can't seem to get into character.
The key is that line.
I still can't figure it out.
"A person like me
doesn't deserve happiness."
That's where I get lost.
From then on,
everything seems to fall apart.
Meaning?
What is the emotion behind this line?
Uh...
Is it like,
"A person like me
doesn't deserve happiness!"
I guess he could be upset.
That makes sense, too.
Should he be suppressing the emotion?
I don't know
if suppress is even the right word.
What is it?
Is it despair?
I don't know how to express it.
Senga has been recognized for his dancing,
but he is taking on this play
with a new determination.
I haven't had much experience as an actor.
What will I create out of this role?
How will I let the role take over me?
What new side of me will I discover?
I guess...
this is more of a mental challenge.
I'm looking forward to finding out.
Senga is rehearsing hard
to get into character.
Just you two brothers alone.
It must have been tough.
A person like me
doesn't deserve happiness.
Eh?
Don't be stupid.
I don't deserve to be happy, ever.
What's gotten into you?
Everyone deserves happiness.
That's right.
On the next Ride On Time,
Kisumai take to the world.
With the use of social media,
people can see Kisumai
from anywhere in the world.
How will their roller-skating fare
on a world stage?
The stage is barely large enough
for us to skate on.
And the opening day
of Busaiku's play finally arrives.
-It's quite different.
-It is?
Subtitle translation by Natsuka Koshimi