NOVEMBER 29, 2019
TAIPEI
Countless fans and cameras
await their arrival.
It's the idol group, Kis-My-Ft2.
They will perform overseas
for the first time.
With the use of social media,
people can see Kisumai
from anywhere in the world.
I want people outside of Japan
to know about us.
I would love to travel
wherever the fans are
and perform for them.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
JULY 2019, KYOCERA DOME OSAKA
TAISUKE FUJIGAYA
HIROMITSU KITAYAMA
Kis-My-Ft2 is a seven-member idol group
on roller skates.
WATARU YOKOO
Also known as "Kisumai."
Over 600,000 fans came
to their five dome tour in 2019.
KENTO SENGA
What makes them different
from other groups
is that they have a unit
within the group.
TOSHIYA MIYATA
BUSAIKU MURA NO WATTO! ODOROKU! DAIISSHO!
The unit is "Busaiku,"
which was formed in 2013.
The four have formed a unique unit
that has blazed an un-idol-like trail.
BUSAIKU
We need to think
about finding our own niche.
Otherwise, we won't have any gigs.
Busaiku is starring in a play
for the first time.
POSTER PHOTO SHOOT
MARUMARU NA HITO NO MATSURO
They break up into two teams,
Yokoo with Senga
and Miyata with Nikaido.
They will play brothers
with a complicated background.
Miyata and Yokoo will play a blind man
who aspires to be a photographer.
What about the photos?
How will I take them?
From up here or down here?
For Miyata, the biggest obstacle
to acting the role of a blind man
is the control of his eye movement.
Really?
This is difficult.
-It is.
-So hard.
"Really?" I can't look at you like this.
Nikaido and Senga
play the younger brother.
Senga is having difficulty
with a particular line.
A person like me
doesn't deserve happiness.
Don't be stupid.
"A person like me
doesn't deserve happiness."
That's where I get lost.
From then on,
everything seems to fall apart.
Uh...
The younger brother feels guilt
towards his elder brother.
But Senga cannot not figure out
how to express it in his acting.
That's how Mom died!
How will they tackle this difficult play?
Late-January, 2020.
With only two weeks to the opening,
the rehearsals are getting serious.
The two combinations of brothers
meet on stage for the first time.
Mom's savings...
The director wants them
to practice together
and be inspired by each other.
Miyata is the elder brother
and Nikaido is the younger brother.
Really? That's good news.
That's how Mom died.
That's not the only reason.
Miyata builds his character
by not making eye contact with anyone.
Hey.
Hisashi?
We'll barely make it on time.
Yokoo watches
how Miyata plays the elder brother.
Sorry. I took too long to get ready.
It's quite different.
-It is?
-Yeah.
You're apologetic to your brother.
When Hisashi says, "I'm doing it for you."
I'd answer back,
"What do you expect? I'm blind!"
-Yeah?
-That's how I acted him.
-Your Toshiyuki is gentle.
-I guess.
My Toshiyuki is mean.
-It reflects our personalities.
-Totally.
Senga is eager to find out
how Nikaido delivers
the line he has been stuck on.
A person like me
doesn't deserve happiness.
Don't be stupid.
I don't deserve to be happy, ever.
However, Senga seems more conflicted.
Let's take a break.
We'll resume at 5:15 p.m...
MITSUTOSHI SAIJO
SCREENPLAY, DIRECTOR
Now that you've seen each other act,
is there anything you want
to go over or discuss?
I have one fundamental problem.
His character development
is different from mine.
I wanted to check with you
whether you want me
to make my version closer to his.
There's no need to make them the same.
We're supposed to have two versions.
You haven't misinterpreted anything.
Keep going as you are.
Understood.
-Let's see how it balances out.
-Got it.
A play about a blind man
and a brother that supports him.
There is a reason why the members want
to portray the roles faithfully.
We had a chance to meet
not necessarily blind,
but visually impaired people.
We had the opportunity to meet
so many people through the Musicthon.
It was Christmas Eve 2019,
two weeks before the rehearsals began.
Traffic lights with audio signals
for the visually impaired.
The 45th Radio Charity Musicthon.
We are live in the studio
in Yurakucho with Kis-My-Ft2.
The phone is ringing off the walls.
Kitayama is sitting with me here.
Musicthon is a 24-hour charity radio event
that calls for donations
to create a more accessible society
for the visually impaired.
Kisumai was the presenter of the show
for two years running.
-Tama-chan?
-Yes?
People are donating.
I can't thank them enough.
You seem very happy.
The members ask for donations
to install traffic lights
with audio signals.
We're doing the Musicthon again this year.
Will you visit us?
Yes!
Visually impaired children
will be visiting the studio.
Adorable.
I heard you guys are practicing a song.
"Awatenbo no Santa Claus."
Also, "Hikari No Signal."
They're practicing our song?
I'm honored.
It is time for the show to wrap up.
Visually impaired children
arrive at the studio.
One, two!
Kento!
-Hello.
As a representative of Kisumai,
Senga will play with the keyboard.
-Hi, everyone.
-Hello.
Did you practice hard?
Yes!
Are you ready?
You'll do fine. I'm nervous.
The children have been
looking forward to this day.
Kento has been practicing, too.
Was that tempo okay?
We went too fast at the start.
The other members arrive.
Now we will perform "Awatenbo no..."
Sorry. Can you all stand?
"Awatenbo no Senga." Hasty Senga.
More hasty than the Santa in the song.
-Hasty Senga.
-A hasty Senga Claus.
I appreciate the jokes, guys.
Thanks.
Are you ready?
-Yes!
-Good.
Now, we'll perform
"Awatenbo no Santa Claus."
Our theme this year is,
"Making people smile."
I hope...
I hope we can build a society
where the visually impaired
can live in safety.
Thank you so much for your support.
Perhaps it difficult for those who can see
to truly understand what it's like
to be visually impaired.
But being a part of Musicthon
changed my mind.
We need to understand.
Why aren't we even trying?
That's what brought me to tears
during the ending speech.
How long has it been?
I haven't cried like that in ages.
FEBRUARY 2020, TOKYO GLOBE ZA
It is opening day for Miyata and Nikaido.
MARUMARU NA HITO NO MATSURO SEA SIDE
Miyata seems to be flustered.
What could be the matter?
My lines have changed
20 minutes before I go on stage.
I can't forget this.
Just two lines.
I'm so flustered.
That's when I screw up the most.
He tells Takashi about the changes.
-Okay. That's it?
-Yep.
-Got it.
-Let's go.
How will he portray a blind man?
DRESSING ROOM D
WATARU YOKOO, TOSHIYA MIYATA
I just do this as a hobby.
Five minutes until the curtain rises.
I'm ready. Let's do this!
It's time.
Miyata and Nikaido take the stage.
I'm exhausted. Are you always this busy?
Guess what?
Yesterday, they asked me
if I wanted to work full-time.
-They did?
-Yeah.
Good for you!
Don't get excited.
Nothing's been decided on yet.
Oh, about that model you were looking for.
Yeah?
I received an e-mail.
You did?
Shall I arrange for us to meet her?
There are things I can feel and do for you
because I am blind.
The play is 130 minutes long.
Miyata portrays the conflict
of a blind man.
You two will make a great couple.
Really? Do you really think so?
Yeah, I do.
Nikaido is there as his younger brother
who encourages him
with honest, caring words.
They're closed.
I know. I'll go somewhere else.
-Be careful.
-I will.
I was worried
about using only sound to act.
However, I have been listening
to Nikaido's voice for years now.
I knew I could count on him.
After acting by just relying on sound,
I was reminded
that Nikaido's voice is
a pleasure to listen to.
Today is the first day
for Yokoo and Senga.
MARUMARU NA HITO NO MATSURO
MOON SIDE
Yokoo is so nervous.
Are you sure? Let me check.
Your hands are so cold!
-One, two!
-Matsuro!
Let's go!
Senga has been struggling
with building his character.
How will he deliver the line today?
Guess what? Yesterday, they asked me
if I wanted to work full-time.
-They did?
-Yeah.
Good for you.
Don't get excited.
Nothing's been decided on yet.
-Yes!
-Aira, can you say something for me?
I need to know where you are.
Okay, then.
Here I am!
-You need to relax a bit more.
-Eh?
I'm a better photographer than you!
-No way!
-I am!
Screw you!
Seriously?
It's time for that line.
He's had it rough, living alone
with his brother since he turned 17.
A person like me
doesn't deserve happiness.
-Don't be stupid.
-Come on!
I don't deserve to be happy, ever.
What's gotten into you?
Everyone deserves happiness.
She's right.
Not me. I can't.
How would he act this short scene?
Senga grappled
with this problem for a month.
Looking back,
I see that I was over-thinking the line.
Yokoo was developing his character, too.
If I make Hisashi too serious,
it doesn't match his Toshiyuki.
When I considered the social dynamics,
it balanced out my character very well.
-Really?
-I didn't notice.
A process of creating
something together as a team.
The members had returned
to their roots without knowing it.
Wonderful company.
Let's keep this up until the end.
-Let's do that.
-Thank you.
Let's get some rest tomorrow.
-Yes.
-We all need it.
We do.
Kisumai took on a new challenge in 2019.
Kitayama was busy preparing for it,
even between magazine photo shoots.
Is that Mandarin?
Yeah.
People around us are doing gigs overseas.
Times are changing.
We need to broaden our horizons, too.
It's also exciting.
What does the future hold for us?
How far will we go?
Even if we fail,
it will be a learning experience for us.
It is Kisumai's
first international performance.
They are scheduled to perform in Taiwan.
How will they be accepted
by the fans in Taiwan?
Wait, which was it?
The members take Mandarin lessons
to prepare for the occasion.
-Eh? "Name?"
-Yes.
How do I say it again?
-"Call?" "Called?"
-That's right.
I came to Taiwan in search of my princess.
I found her! It's you!
Nice. I like it.
What do you think? Will they like it?
-They will.
-Great!
-Yeah.
-Please teach me this.
And?
Other groups have performed
in Taiwan before them.
Kisumai must make a strong
and lasting impression, too.
Do I pause after that?
Yes. You should add a pause.
I can't wait until the event.
The floor will be filled by the audience.
I wonder how it will turn out.
I hope we can communicate directly
with the people we meet.
On the next Ride On Time,
Kisumai arrives in Taiwan.
We are Kis-My-Ft2.
The members give their all
to gain recognition.
Will they be able to impress
with their roller skates?
It'll depend on
whether we can build up speed.
I haven't been this nervous in ages.
What's gotten into me?
Subtitle translation by Natsuka Koshimi