THIS SUMMER THEY LOST SOMEONE DEAR TO THEM
AND STARTED A NEW JOURNEY
If we hadn't learned
what we did from Mr. Johnny...
YUTA KISHI (24)
I don't know what
we would've been doing now...
I hope we're powerful enough
that it reaches Mr. Johnny.
He gave me constructive criticism
until the very end.
YUTA JINGUJI (21)
He wouldn't say I was bad,
just suggest a better way.
He said he'd be watching me.
He really was watching.
But that made me happy.
He told me that
I would find out
my own strengths one day.
I want to always keep that in mind
and be able to tell Mr. Johnny
that I'm confident in myself.
I don't think Mr. Johnny
would want that.
REN NAGASE (20)
He wouldn't want people
crying for him.
If I ever...
see him on the other side,
I want to make sure
I haven't disappointed Mr. Johnny.
He said my first name
could be spelled "Show"
as in show business
and entertainment.
At first, I didn't understand
what he was talking about,
but now, I feel like it was my destiny.
Actually...
I almost feel like I was destined
to meet Mr. Johnny
ever since my parents named me Sho.
It feels like fate.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
Last January,
the debut of a group was announced.
King & Prince.
It's my first time doing this,
so I'm nervous.
They still had a childlike
innocence about them.
MAY 26,2018
ODAIBA PALETTE PLAZA
But they powerfully
marched forward,
and rose to stardom.
AUG. 10, 2018
YOKOHAMA ARENA
Yokohama Arena kicked off
their unprecedented first concert tour
that spanned across five cities
with twenty-one performances.
DEC. 31, 2018
They even performed at
Kohaku Uta Gassen.
-Good work.
-Yes.
-I'm tired.
-Hello.
-We watched you guys.
I do feel pressure
doing any type of work, honestly.
Now that we've debuted,
it's to be expected.
For the bartender role...
They will face the challenges
of their second year.
The leader, Yuta Kishi,
struggles with his role as a talk show MC.
Anna, this is your―
-That's terrible!
-Sorry!
The youngest member, Kaito Takahashi,
also debuts as a manga artist.
Good evening! I am...
Ren Nagase, the group's MC from Kansai,
hones his skills on the radio.
The volleyball club...
They all have big boobs for some reason.
The frontman of the group, Sho Hirano,
appears in movies
and variety shows, one after another.
And the organizer of the group,
Yuta Jinguji,
is now getting involved with
the concert's stage production.
A story based on the lyrics.
-We can do that.
-You can?
We can.
They've raised their game
and started another concert tour.
Their second year as King & Prince.
We'll reflect on their days
of determination.
April...
On this day, they were shooting
their new music video.
It smells like...
I'm at a concert.
They appear in costumes
that differ in style
from those in their first year.
It's cold.
They're wearing mostly black.
MARCH 15, 2018
ROPPONGI, TOKYO
In their first year,
their songs, dances, and costumes
had a prince-like style.
This time, they will take on
a song with a mature air.
Wait, this is hard.
This is hard.
Most of the lyrics are in English.
I wasn't ready to use my brain
this morning.
Okay, should we try?
-All right!
-Show your stomachs!
Yes!
Music please.
To show a new side of them,
they've changed
their style of dancing as well.
They dance a sexy, hip-hop style routine
for the entire song that is
three and a half minutes long.
Although they break it up
into several parts to film,
it is quite the workout.
This is bad...
-Ten-minute break.
-Okay.
My heart is going to give out.
This is tiring.
This is...
just exhausting.
They've just learned the routine.
Though filming part by part,
the members are spent
just trying not to mess up.
But the staff...
We'll do one long take.
What did you say?
One long take.
All or nothing.
-Are you serious?
-I am.
-Will it be on the DVD?
-I'll add it in.
I'd like that.
If we can do it.
-I see.
-It's one shot?
-All or nothing.
-I know, right?
The last chorus...
Can they dance for
three and a half minutes with no mistakes?
We can definitely do it.
I believe in myself.
Okay.
Let's do our best and dance.
-Yeah.
-Kinpuri Fighters, let's go!
Yeah!
Kinpuri Fighters...
What is Kinpuri Fighters?
-Music please.
-Okay.
ABOUT 1 MINUTE IN
ABOUT 2 MINUTES IN
ABOUT THREE MINUTES IN
AFTER ABOUT 3 MINUTES AND 30 SECONDS
Cut!
Good work!
Their goal is to one day
make it big overseas,
so it is necessary that
they up their game in every aspect.
That was good.
I'm so tired.
So tired!
Our desire has become stronger.
-In a good way.
-Almost like a craving?
Everyone has their own focus.
Ren is doing the costumes,
Kaito does dance routines and production,
Jinguji looks at the overall picture,
and so do I.
Hey! Find something for me!
At least include me
in that group with you!
I almost didn't catch that.
-Just say all three of us do that.
-I ran out of ideas.
I don't blame you.
I was searching for a focus myself.
Without things like that...
The weight that Hirano carries...
was revealed to us
when we spent two days with him.
KAGUYA-SAMA: LOVE IS WAR
Since his debut,
this is already his second time
starring in a film.
Thank you for waiting.
Hello.
He is swamped with movie promotions.
A lot of people said that
my ditzy side comes out in the character.
Since there are a lot of people
who are fans of the original work,
I want those people to find it
entertaining as well.
Thank you.
The lead actor of a film has the weighty
responsibility of making it a hit.
In these two days, he was interviewed
by 29 media outlets.
Take it and then check it.
Over there.
Photo shoots and interviews
were scheduled one after another.
WEEKLY YOUNG JUMP PHOTO SHOOT
Early morning on the second day...
It's like waterfall meditation.
Okay. That's great.
What they wanted was
to see his typical idol side.
-You're early today.
-Huh?
-You were here earlier than me.
Wow...
I haven't seen you act
this idol-like in so long.
-How rude.
-No, no.
-I am an idol.
-I know.
You haven't seen me be idol-like?
We always see you, so...
Hirano seems to be in high spirits,
but in an interview after this,
he says something unexpected.
That's true...
I was on a live music TV program yesterday
and I met a lot of my seniors.
Some were skilled at talking,
some were skilled actors, and so on.
I thought to myself, what is going to be
my skill as a Johnny's member?
All the members
do separate jobs, you know?
As I wondered
what field I should focus on,
I became anxious and fell asleep.
Yeah.
I know...
I haven't...
His body was
reacting honestly to his emotions.
I try to drink something warm
to take care of my throat.
By the way, Kishi said...
It may be from fatigue,
but he was getting a rash.
That's what they told me
at the hospital.
I wonder if lack of sleep has something
to do with it too.
I easily get sick after a big job.
My body lets its guard down.
After I get off stage we do...
Was it called san-san-nana?
The sanbonjime cheer?
Yeah, sanbonjime.
I've gone straight to the hospital without
even doing our sanbonjime post-show cheer.
The other day,
I was throwing up backstage too.
I will be careful not to let
my immune system get weak.
And still,
as long as there's a camera filming him...
Good morning.
Thank you.
Why are you still filming?
In documentaries,
they film people walking away.
-Oh, I understand.
-No, no, no.
-Thank you.
How embarrassing.
The other members are also
feeling the pressure just like him.
Today, they are learning the dance
for their other new song, "Koi-Wazurai."
Because all of the members are busy
and they don't have much time to practice,
each one gets
their own professional dancer
to teach them.
One more time.
One, two...
Okay, in thirty minutes,
we'll try running through it
-together as a group.
-Yes.
-We'll take a break...
-Oh, no.
-...and meet in 30.
-My brain is fried.
Even during break time,
the one who is diligently practicing
is Kishi.
He continues to dance without resting.
Hey, Kishi. You should take a break.
-Your focus―
-I'm fine.
I'm good.
-You should use the restroom.
-I went.
-You went? What about a drink?
-Yes.
-Are you okay?
-Wow.
-Let's go.
-Just once.
All right. For how many minutes?
Three minutes.
Jinguji stops him,
and he finally takes a break.
-He's amazing.
-He is.
Kishi puts a lot of pressure on himself.
"If I cut corners, I won't make it."
He lives by those words.
Let's redo it and fix what's difficult.
-Man...
-Okay.
This year, I want to one-up
all the things that we did last year.
I want to hone our skills,
or more like evolve
in everything we do this year.
MIKKAI RESTAURANT
FILMING
Just as he said,
this year he is trying out
something new.
-It's my first time, so...
-Right.
I'm nervous but I'll do my best.
-For this part...
-Yes?
...I wait until they speak?
Yes. You can laugh.
-That's no problem.
-Okay.
He was chosen to be an MC
for a talk show.
The rehearsal for Kishi
from King & Prince.
Thank you.
-Now, you...
-Yes?
...stir it once.
While engaging in conversation,
he must make the drinks
for the guests on the show.
-You stir it like that...
-Once you do...
-Then...
-Yes.
Today's snack is
Nyokinyoki Printemps.
In the little time he has,
he studies the script.
We can use funny mistakes.
-It's okay.
-I'll try to make funny mistakes.
Today, you're like the facilitator.
That's right.
Me, out of all people.
It's my first time taking on
a role like this
on a talk show.
I'm going to pee my pants.
At first, I thought
they asked the wrong person.
But I'm so grateful that I got this.
I really want to be able to
live up to their expectations.
Yeah.
Four, three,
two...
FILMING STARTS
Like that, they begin to film.
Surrounded by people
like his fellow MC who's an actress
and other popular TV personalities...
His first words are...
Anna, this is your―
-That's terrible!
-Sorry!
I know, I wasn't sure
when I should chime in.
It's so sudden.
I'm sorry, I'm still in training.
-This is your third marriage?
-Yes.
How are you when you're in love?
It's not an interview!
I was just very curious.
I like his awkwardness.
Well,
I fall in love with...
Right now, everything he does is training.
"One hundred percent.
Yuta always gives one hundred percent."
I'm ending all of them with this phrase.
The one who drew Kishi in his manga
was the youngest member,
Kaito Takahashi.
KAITO TAKAHASHI (20)
Last year, Takahashi
participated in a project for aspiring
manga artists in a monthly magazine.
This time,
he will start a comic strip series.
BETSUCOMI SERIES
JOHNNY'S AND ME
Try it on him.
So dark.
He's so tanned now.
The theme for his comic strip is...
If an idol is going to draw it,
I thought our fans would enjoy
reading about the daily life of an idol.
An idol writing a manga series.
That made news
and attracted many interviewers
who came to the announcement.
Can you hold up the print?
This time when you decided...
For Takahashi,
this should be a happy event...
The next story?
But as they keep asking questions,
he is starting to look anxious.
Already, from the first one,
they're talking about deadlines and stuff.
From here, because of our line of work,
we'll start getting
long-term jobs and such.
Whether that's theater
or tours...
When that happens, I'll probably have to
come home after a tiring day
of being on stage
and work on my manga without sleeping.
When I think about that,
I'm so afraid of the future.
I didn't think I'd be doing a series.
But you know,
you are a professional manga artist.
Now, I have to work hard.
Today, I'm going to...
Takahashi will end up facing a crisis
just a few days later.
SHOGAKUKAN
A few days after his new series
was announced...
-Good morning.
Takahashi was again
at the publishing company
to work on his series.
He looks exhausted.
Damn it...
-He hurt his back.
-What?
Yes...
He says it hurts in any position.
Is it a slipped disc?
-That's what they told me.
-Or fatigue?
He said it just happened suddenly
while he was filming a show.
A slipped disc at my age
is caused by tiredness and fatigue,
supposedly.
I was like, "Don't say I have
a slipped disc when I'm this young."
But my body has enough power
to heal in two to three days.
I'm a Johnny's member.
-Let's do this.
-Let's.
Five pages.
By the end of today,
he must finish at least the rough drafts
of seven comic strips.
However...
-On the right...
-Ouch.
Oh, no... I can't think at all.
What should I do...
But the deadline will not wait for him.
Damn, it really hurts.
I can't...
There is both joy and pain
that comes from everyone's expectations.
While writhing in pain,
he keeps his pen moving.
And two hours later...
I can't think of anything
for the last one.
The last one?
Just a little more.
He is done.
JULY 2019
TOKYO
Then came July,
when they lost someone dear to them.
The five King & Prince members
are rehearsing with
their backup Johnny's Jr. dancers
for their new upcoming tour.
Five, six, seven, eight...
They're trying to
live up to the expectations
of the man who hated somber atmospheres.
On the next Ride On Time...
If we use white denim,
the bottom can...
The members themselves build up
the tour for their second year.
The audience here can't see very well.
During rehearsal,
something happens to one member.
My foot hurts.
What's the reason why
they keep charging forward?
If we don't push ourselves past our limit,
it won't be a cool performance.
Right before showtime...
Is this the real speed?
The entertainment legacy gets passed down.
There, we'll see
a new side to King & Prince.
Subtitle translation by Kiko Morita