-Let's do this.
-Okay.
Ready, go!
-Awesome!
-Well?
A performer in his 25th year
at Johnny's...
Tomoyuki Yara.
Right now,
he is taking onthe kind of entertainment
that he has dedicated his life to.
All right!
-Yeah!
-That went well!
I'm so nervous.
Its name? THE YOUNG LOVE DISCOTHEQUE.
Starting with the 1970s disco scene,
the music and dances from a variety
of periods are recreated,
inviting the audience into another world.
It's a time and space for everyone
to lose themselves in dance.
All of this is being upheld
by Yara's stoicism.
I doubt I'll ever be satisfied
with my dancing.
As long as I'm doing this job,
I never will be.
That's why I crave to do things like this.
ORIGINAL MUSICAL
THE CIRCUS! EPISODE FINAL
Yara's starred as an actor
in over ten stage productions.
He's also appeared in a show
notoriously hard to get tickets for,
Endless SHOCK.
He's played the role of the rival,
Koichi Domoto, for many years.
When it comes to choreography, as well,
he's worked on songs for countless groups
and is trusted completely
by his Johnny's comrades.
He's really skilled, really cool,
and has great taste, I think.
Someone who specializes in dance?
I'm sure there's nobody else like him.
In the agency,
the number of people who look up to him
is considerable.
If you can choose who you're going
to work with,
it's always, "Yara!"
YUMA NAKAYAMA
He's detailed, works you hard,
and makes no compromises.
He spends the time necessary
to make something good,
and I admire him for that drive.
Surprisingly, however,
Yara has long been torn
between forging his own path
and living the life of an idol.
You get impatient.
I mean, at my age,
there's no chance, right?
Don't you think?
I'm signed with Johnny's,
I'm an idol...
And I'm still doing that at the age of 36.
It still makes me go, "Huh?"
Despite having his doubts,
he continues to believe.
His goal
is a new realm of expression
using dance as its weapon.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
CAST AND CREW MEETING
This will be THE YOUNG LOVE DISCOTHEQUE's
third show since it first premiered.
The members and crew have gathered today.
I want to make it more stylish.
So, we need to think about
the sense of speed.
My goal this time
is an aggressive DISCOTHEQUE.
KEITA RICHAED KUSAMA
As the show's general producer,
Yara has assembled members
from among his trusted
junior Johnny's members.
BUNICHI HAMANAKA
He's also recruited backup dancers
for famous singers,
and professional dancers
who've worked as choreographers.
ITSUKA
And putting the music together
for the live show
are rappers and DJs who've made
an impact on the Japanese scene.
Assistant director MAEDA
is one of the performers in whom
Yara has placed most of his trust.
Meanwhile, someone who is perhaps
appearing to not be so reliable
is Yukihiro Suetake,
only in his fourth year as a Johnny's Jr.
Then you stand your left leg up
and put this on it.
Then wrap it around your ankle.
Then one, two.
Then tense your stomach
and swing your left leg back.
That creates this motion.
As that happens,
make your belly touch the floor.
Yes!
Spin your legs around.
As you did that,
your left leg didn't swing.
You stop halfway which makes you
have to use your strength to spin.
Swing! Then your legs move on their own.
Swing! That's it.
Show me your cartwheel.
You're joking!
Seriously?
Suetake doesn't even have experience
as a backup dancer yet.
I've only done basic dancing.
Just doing this the whole time.
-That can't be true!
-Really.
I don't do these crazy moves.
So, it's a bit new for me.
I mean, everything's new for me.
Nevertheless, Yara has a reason
to bring in the young juniors especially.
I'm asking you to do a variety of things,
Suetake.
The 1980s dances and the break dancing.
The 1970s,
like the soul dancing and so on.
You can see all kinds of videos
of them now, like on YouTube.
I want you to watch them
and get a feel for the atmosphere.
Yes.
What I most want is
for you to be conscious
of standing at the front of the stage
as a lone artist.
-That's the big thing.
-Yes.
That's more important than the technique.
In addition to directing
and choreographing,
Yara also has work to do as a performer.
I've received a video of a routine.
So, I'll have to practice it
until it sinks in.
I'm watching a video by myself
to memorize it.
-It's dull work.
-No, it's amazing.
-Can you tell what's going on?
-Not really.
This is so difficult.
This job really is fun, though.
So, you know...
It's a collaboration
with a top dance team.
One, two. Oh, damn!
It's fast.
I can't decipher it.
-Hello.
-I should have it down.
-Really?
Amazing!
I only had the film,
so I don't have the little details.
Sure.
This is the dance team, 9stepper'z!!
Yara will be dancing a routine
that saw them place
in Japan's biggest contest.
Way to go!
Brilliant!
You're kidding me.
Awesome!
-We could never do that!
-That was great.
It's amazing how fast he learns.
How long did it take?
When did we send it to him?
-Last week?
-It was last week.
-Not even two weeks ago?
-Thursday two weeks ago, maybe.
But it was more or less perfect
when we got here today.
We just had to do the little touches.
It's amazing, learning from a video.
We had to do the formation, too.
That was it.
He's the real deal.
He's a Johnny's idol.
So, how do top dancers like you feel
about taking part
in an event like this?
How do we feel?
We're absolutely thrilled.
I was struck by going
to the Johnny's offices.
"This is Johnny's agency!" I thought.
Yara's attention went to street dance
due to one person's music.
Good morning.
-Here we are.
-Wow!
This is how much music he listens to.
-Incredible.
-Yeah.
This is amazing.
I like this.
This is m.c.A.T, who'll be
working on the DISCOTHEQUE music.
As they are going to be making
original dance music for each era,
he is the only man for the job.
In terms of my career,
I never thought
I'd get to team up with Yara
in any of my lines of work.
I was very keen and interested at first,
but I wasn't sure it was going to work.
But then,
Yara eased my concerns by saying
we could work in all sorts of places,
and that he wanted to work with me.
And then it got going.
That made a big impression.
The thing is, with DISCOTHEQUE...
Well, I've always liked street dance
since I was a teenager.
And if it wasn't for street dance,
I'm not sure I would have been able
to make what I've made.
And ever since I was around 20,
I've had this idea
of somehow doing something with it.
Have you been this into dancing
all through your time at Johnny's?
Well, you know...
I just did the routines I was given
and tried to look my best, I guess.
I wasn't seeking out new techniques
or anything.
If anything,
I was more concerned about my hair.
I had a phase like that.
I would try to make my hair
look the best I could.
But since I came across A.T's music,
I've been more interested
in furthering my dance technique.
That sent me this way.
But...
I lived a tiresome life
at Johnny's for a while, actually.
At the age of 12,
Yara walked through Johnny's doors.
Among his contemporaries
were Hideaki Takizawa
and people who would go on
to be in ARASHI.
When they were Jr.s, he and Sho Sakurai
were in similar positions.
Rock dancing was the main focus
of Johnny's back then.
He said he wanted to do something
a little different, like hip-hop or house.
I remember the two of us
often watching VHS tapes together.
Becoming obsessed with dance,
Yara strayed from the idol route.
But that hasn't faded at all to this day.
And it's likely because it hasn't faded
that I was able to make this show.
It's been a long road.
I've thought about giving up
dozens of times.
Yeah.
THE CIRCUS! PHOTOSHOOT
Most of the work he's offered now
is for musicals.
He's already been cast in the lead roles
for two shows this year.
That's it! Okay!
To expand his range, he's also
applied himself to singing and acting.
Yeah! Okay! Yeah!
It has some sexiness to it.
It's a good one, isn't it?
Involved in this show's production
is a dance teacher who's seen Yara grow.
He's a rare kind of person.
Someone who likes dance but is an idol.
You don't ever see that.
You do.
I haven't introduced you yet.
Jeez, this guy...
I was saying all nice things about you.
Really?
Just when you think he's gone,
he always turns up.
He really likes dancing.
I got really into TETSUHARU's dances.
They're so cool,
but I couldn't come every time.
His manager would bring him to one,
but then he'd miss the next one.
I guess that's how it is with idols,
but he came of his own volition, too.
After much hard work, he got DISCOTHEQUE.
They've reached the climax of the show
in their practice sessions.
It's an open, exposed show.
I said we could do
whatever we wanted here, didn't I?
Their practice has gotten
to the show's climax.
I messed up!
Is it easier to spin that way?
One more time.
He wants to convey to his juniors
that if you like dance,
anyone can perform like the star
of the show in this kind of entertainment.
Again. Good morning!
-Sorry.
-Good morning.
Sorry.
That's why the greater the gap
between their technique and a pro's,
the more he wants them to consider
how to express themselves through dance.
Put more "oomph" into your kick there.
Yes.
He'd hoped to have gotten this
through to them many times,
but he still doesn't see it
in their attitude.
Hoping to create an opportunity for this,
he's making everyone undress.
It's about exposure.
All right! Let's go!
I'll count you in.
Look for what you find cool.
Like this.
-Everyone does this differently.
-Yeah.
It's fine if some of you
are just doing that,
but if that's all you ever do,
it's not interesting.
It's a bit stiff.
NEW JACK SWING:
POPULAR LATE '80s, EARLY '90s
For the new jack swing dance
they're currently mastering,
it's not so much the precision
of the routine that's key,
but the groove that each dancer has.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Can I record you one time?
-That was awful.
-Okay, sorry!
Absolutely awful.
They're not getting anywhere.
Yara is fretting.
Have you been ill?
Ill?
I'm fine.
How can he explain it to his juniors?
I wonder what we should do.
Are you aware of what you're doing?
Are you doing what you've been asked
and giving it your best shot?
Listen, everyone.
You don't need to be in perfect time
with each other.
Do you want to come out as a group,
like, "Boom!"?
With this level of excitement,
you're not living up to the song.
You could do with some research.
Watch how they danced in the '90s
to new jack swing.
Then I think this routine
will come together.
Your grooves need to be together.
It's not about the exact moves,
but having the same rhythm.
You need to do your own research.
I doubt you're looking into
how you can make yourselves
look good with this.
Watch.
Nothing's changing like this.
Not from what you've been doing.
So, I want you to show me that.
Every time a new dance is taken on,
days are spent searching for footage
to the point of exhaustion.
That's what made Yara what he is.
Mae-chan made this routine for this music,
so, I just want you to enjoy the dancing.
Didn't I say I wanted to see
how Yukihiro Suetake looked
as a lone artist?
The same goes for Richard and Bun-chan.
You don't have to match,
but you need to come together
to make this DISCOTHEQUE.
That's what I want.
It's you guys who have to bring
that something extra.
I really want you
to have a think about that.
I don't get it. I just don't.
-Not even after watching the video.
-No?
I'll just have to do it.
Because watching hasn't helped me.
Because I don't know how to dance to it,
it's more confusing than it is fun
at the moment.
I don't have the rhythm down.
So, this isn't good enough
to go on stage yet?
Not for me, no. Definitely not.
-Definitely not?
-Definitely not.
They should...
be having fun themselves.
But they're not convincing me
that they are.
That's all it is.
They have to work the rest out
for themselves.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Once they do,
it should make a world of difference.
Will Yara's feelings...
get through to them?
The day of the first show
finally comes around.
There's no time to change.
Just come on like that!
Do your best in the battle.
Keep battling a little more.
So long as you have an attitude of attack,
it's sure to be thrilling.
Johnny's can't be taken lightly.
Not at all.
The performance
he's devoted his life to begins.
Subtitle translation by Lewis Williams