One youth is pushing himself
to his limit to become someone new.
I can't get any help?
You have to do it yourself.
You have to. No other way.
Another youth is
watching over his friends
as he fights for someone else.
This balance is good.
I agree.
These two were about to begin
their challenge.
This is documentary series Ride On Time.
King & Prince's second year
since debuting has begun.
Their performances have scaled up.
They're now showing a new mature
and sexy side to them.
They're looking toward their future.
I want to hurry up and make it overseas,
so we can show him.
He said, "You guys can do it."
I'll put my faith in those words.
2019...
They were encouraged
by someone dear to them
and were given a big responsibility.
Yuta Kishi
and Yuta Jinguji.
These two will...
be a part of the stage play Dream Boys.
It's a masterpiece that has been
performed by countless seniors.
Will I be able to see
you two competing again?
It is a story about boys
who are childhood friends,
and how they overcome many conflicts
and mature through boxing.
What's the difference?!
From now on,
we'll create our future together.
It features acrobatic performances
and is very taxing.
DREAM BOYS PRESS CONFERENCE
The number of reporters
who came to the press conference
reflects the expectations
put on Jinguji and Kishi.
At first, we were terrified
when Mr. Johnny told us.
That's right. We were like, "Us!?"
It's crazy.
Will these two succeed
in overcoming this large obstacle?
They begin their practice.
This side is the audience,
so try not to turn your back to it.
The two of you...
First, they begin with
the main focus of the story, boxing.
Of course, they have no experience.
It's tiring, huh?
It sure is.
What's most important,
is to make it look real.
Will they be able to pull the viewers
into the story?
That is the key.
I don't want to look like a novice.
Kishi has one more challenge
that he must take up
with that same mindset.
The strings are really old.
In this play, he must play the guitar,
which he has no experience with,
and sing a solo part.
-Oh, just this one?
-Yeah.
They only have one month
until opening day.
Kishi has begun pushing himself
to his limit again.
OSAKA-JO HALL
Even during their tour,
he had Jinguji, who can play the guitar,
teach him.
I see. The strumming...
His hands were constantly on the guitar.
Even on their way to the stage...
-See you. I'm Guitar Samurai.
-You're taking that?
END OF SHOW
At one point, we even saw him like this.
Good work.
Thank you.
You're already holding a guitar?
They're looking good. A novice's...
A novice's blister.
Will he be ready by opening day?
Let's do a match.
Meanwhile...
-That's reckless!
-Shut up.
Jinguji was feeling the pressure
during acting lessons.
The script isn't ready.
Are you guys in a time crunch?
-It's tight.
-Yeah?
It's a tight schedule.
This time, he will be playing
a champion who wants to fight
in the ring despite his head injury.
It is a difficult role.
As someone who fought, I know.
Act like you're worried about him.
Sit down.
Not only does he have to
portray serious emotions,
he must overcome one more hurdle.
Look...
it's important to never give up.
At the end of the stage play,
there is a Show Time slot.
Right after they act out a serious role,
they must entertain the audience even more
with a performance
including song and dance.
IMPERIAL THEATRE
On this day,
one of their seniors visited
the theater rehearsal room.
A line that conveys what is in your hearts
to the audience.
Kinki Kids member,
Koichi Domoto.
He is the chairman of Endless SHOCK,
a stage play that has had
over 1,700 showings.
This theater expert has volunteered
to help with the stage production.
As the two of them
nervously listen to his words,
Domoto suddenly brings up
the Show Time slot.
I don't think so.
Do we really need the Show Time?
Doing that as a form of fan service
is kind of a must for Johnny's theater.
That's how I feel.
I don't think Mr. Johnny would say that.
He told me if the main act is good,
you don't need Show Time.
-What do they want to show?
-Right...
-It's about what you want to show.
-Okay.
Will they be able to satisfy
the audience without Show Time?
It's good that you're contemplating.
They care about their fans.
Nothing like Koichi back in the day.
What Domoto wanted to relay to them
was the importance of
thinking on their own
and deciding on their own.
In order to stand on their own
as performers,
that is the most important thing.
FOR DREAM BOYS
Actually, this time,
there was a performance
that Kishi requested himself.
That's good.
It involved this cube.
Controlling the movements of this cube
is quite hard.
It takes a lot of muscle.
-Just do a little at a time.
-Yes.
Bring your hand closer to your face.
He loses track of time
and immerses himself in practice.
Sweat drips down his back.
This is no good.
My hands aren't working.
You're probably very tired today.
That's true.
-You have to keep aiming higher.
-Right, higher.
That's the minimum requirement.
-The minimum.
-Yes.
-I'll work on that.
-That's good.
I want to go higher.
-Like this?
-Right.
He doesn't just twirl the cube.
They also use it in the flying routine.
-Oh, no!
-It's okay.
He must support this cube
with just his neck.
Okay.
Just in case the cube falls,
they planned to have female performers
below him as insurance.
However...
Can I give you my opinion?
I want him to get through it alone.
Without any help.
-Without help?
-Yes.
-You have to take the risk.
-I agree.
They're not your mothers.
-I can't get any help?
-You have to do it yourself.
You have to. No other way.
I see.
Jinguji was watching over Kishi.
Nishikiori once said that he thought
theater was a boat.
The entire cast is on the ship.
No one can just get off the boat.
We're all stuck there.
Once you leave port, you can't go back.
All of you
have to make it to the goal.
That is how theater is.
Go.
Being on the same boat
and sharing the same fate...
That applies to King & Prince
as a group as well.
The two of them can work hard
because no matter
how difficult things are,
they have each other,
members who are determined
to survive the rough waters together.
Ready...
DRAMA SHOOTING
In the extreme heat,
exceeding 35 degrees Celsius,
Nagase is starring in a drama.
-It's so hot.
-I need tape over here.
But he is determined
to keep a smile on his face.
I'm with the other actors
and actresses the whole time,
so I want to create
a positive atmosphere on set.
That's what I'm aiming for.
Ready...
Go.
Another member
who faced a challenge on set
was Kaito Takahashi.
He is acting alongside his senior,
Shori Sato,
and trying to live up to
everyone's expectations.
Cut.
-Was that good?
-Okay.
His role is that of
an energetic high-school boy.
Chuya.
However...
-Chuya.
-Yes, I'm Chuya Tsukioka!
I made it in time. That was close.
Cut.
-The general flow was good.
-Okay.
That just looked like
a regular kid who's late.
I want you to almost
start a Chuya Tsukioka show.
Naturally,
I'm not a very energetic person.
-Five times more energetic.
-Five?
Be conscious of that
and it will be just right.
-Tsukioka.
-Yes, I'm Chuya Tsukioka!
I made it in time. That was close.
-Chuya Tsukioka.
-Yes!
I'm Chuya Tsukioka! I made it in time.
That was close.
Cut.
Okay.
He somehow got it down.
Hey!
Good morning.
Yesterday...
I was up late working on my manga.
I was supposed to work on it today too,
but I finished it yesterday.
I'll survive with fighting spirit.
Each of the members are
fighting their own battles.
Oh, no...
-Was I sleeping?
-Just for a bit.
PORT MESSE NAGOYA
They were on tour at the same time.
What can they do
to make their fans even happier?
They keep trying new things.
We were talking about it earlier,
but during "Betsubetsu no Sora,"
would it be too much
to dance in the aisle?
MAKOMANAI SEKISUI HEIM ICE ARENA
On this day, Hirano and Kishi
visited the local staff in Hokkaido.
-We want to learn the dialect.
-Dialect?
-Namara?
-Namara.
-Oh, like "namara good."
-Like, "seriously good."
-Osasatta.
-Osasatta?
-Like, "time has osasatta."
-Meaning, "time has flown"?
-Thank you.
-No problem.
-Oshitatta?
-Osasatta.
Osasatta.
-Osasatta and namara. Thank you.
-No problem.
Namara, osatatta.
Was it oshitatta?
Kishi-kun
More, Kishi-kun
Namara be mine.
I namara want to hold you.
With their fans,
they continue on their voyage
on this boat called
King & Prince.
As they rehearse for Dream Boys,
Kishi looks especially happy.
-I bought a guitar.
-Huh?
-Really?
Did you splurge?
I couldn't help it.
A guitar made by a famous manufacturer.
He is known to be a frugal person,
but he splurged in order to
raise his own morale.
-That's a really nice guitar.
-That's why I have to get better.
-Each player has a unique sound.
-I see.
-That's good.
-Okay.
Their rehearsals are coming to an end,
and today is the scene
that talks about the importance of dreams.
People can't live without dreams.
But dreams don't always come true.
What's important...
Domoto, who's helping
with the production, is there.
Some don't come true.
You became number one
in the harsh world of boxing.
When you say,
"in the harsh world of boxing",
right here,
it doesn't really reach the heart.
Saying "in the harsh world of boxing" here
-creates a world of boxing right there.
-Okay.
If you do that, the listeners empathize
-with the lines better.
-Okay.
That may be better.
At that moment, Kishi...
Then it clicks in my mind
that I don't care.
At that moment,
-can I be like this?
-You can stand. Of course.
I don't care about winning.
"I want to stand and deliver my line."
Kishi proposed his own idea.
You became number one
in the harsh world of boxing.
I don't care about winning.
As long as we can...
use our gloves
to recover our bond that was broken.
That was much better.
-I'll go with that then.
-Perfect.
Let's do that.
Thinking and deciding on his own.
He was able to take one step forward.
Take the net away.
Opening day is nearing.
Don't let go.
IMPERIAL THEATRE
It's opening day for the stage play,
Dream Boys.
-Good morning.
Jinguji looks the same as usual.
On the other hand, Kishi...
-Your throat?
-What?
My throat's sensitive.
I see.
It's rare to see him with a sore throat.
Good morning.
He was holding an inhaler
to care for his throat.
Stage rehearsal will begin in ten minutes.
This is seriously bad.
Good morning.
Despite that,
he begins the final check.
I had a fever the other day,
-and my throat never recovered.
-I see.
It's so raspy.
Sorry.
That wasn't all.
Can we make it colored?
He suddenly started feeling pain
in his left arm.
TEN MINUTES UNTIL SHOWTIME
Still...
YUTA JINGUJI, YUTA KISHI
No matter what his condition is,
he will stand on stage.
Because that's what he was taught
by the person he holds dear
and his seniors.
-Break a leg.
-Excuse me.
The stage play,
Dream Boys,
is about to raise the curtains.
The time has come.
They both went down to 55 kg
and built up their bodies.
As he promised,
he did the cube by himself.
The guitar which he never put down...
The characters they've each built up...
You became number one
in the harsh world of boxing.
I don't care about winning.
As long as we can use our gloves
to recover our bond that was broken.
Look...
it's important to never give up.
No matter what happens,
you can never give up.
You want to become the champion, right?
And the finale...
They both decided to do the Show Time.
They finished the show with a performance
that lured in the audience.
-Thank you for coming today.
-Let's meet again.
Thank you.
It was fun.
Some scenes gave me goosebumps
as I was acting.
It was an amazing experience.
And Kishi...
Thank you.
I'm sure Mr. Johnny was watching.
I did everything I could to perform
in a way that would get his approval.
I think I was able to perform
with my head held high.
I'll work even harder.
-There's still more.
-Yes.
-Thank you.
Good work.
That spirit...
is passed on to them next.
I do feel like
I don't want to lose to them.
These three will guide the large boat
and depart.
TOMOYUKI YARA (36)
Next time, it's Tomoyuki Yara.
As one of Johnny's best dancers,
what is this lone performer
going up against?
I don't want Johnny's members
to be looked down on.
He is the one-and-only member
who specializes in dancing, I believe.
In his 25th year as a Johnny's member,
what is his resolve?
He spends all of his time
trying to perfect whatever he does,
and I fell in love with his perseverance.
He aims for the biggest stage
in the world.
If you take away dance,
I will have nothing left.
Subtitle translation by Kiko Morita