XANDER: I'm slowly
venting oxygen.
[SIGHS]
All my training is telling me
that I should stop speaking
so as to conserve
my remaining air,
but I don't think that
anybody's gonna find me in time.
I need there to be a record
for the unlikely event that my
body is ever discovered, so...
The green plasma energy
that we encountered
appears to be some sort of
anti-matter super-weapon.
It... it consumed
the freighter that we were on,
and from what I observed...
From what I... from what I can...
[SOBS]
But none of that really matters
anymore, does it?
Now, it's funny, I'm, uh...
I'm looking at the stars...
I'm looking into
the void of space,
and all that infinite beauty
can't compare to you... Jax.
[♪♪]
You're the first thing
that I see when I wake up
in the morning,
and you're the last thing
that I think of
when I fall asleep.
And now...
[SIGHS] ...as I close my eyes
for what very well
might be the final time...
Warning. Warning.
- ...it's you...
- Warning.
- ...now...
Warning. Warning.
...and always.
Looks like you could use
some help there, Captain.
- Computer, erase recording.
- [BEEPING]
[THEME MUSIC]
I still can't believe
that you found me in time.
Dauntless
is no ordinary ship,
but you knew that already.
You're no ordinary woman,
but I should think
you knew that as well.
But I never get tired
of hearing it.
Welcome aboard, Captain.
How are you feeling?
I'm just happy
to have a pulse, Admiral.
Well, you can thank
Cadet Zhou for that.
We knew the star system
where the freighter was lost.
Somehow, Jax had a sixth sense
that you were still alive out there,
and was able to pinpoint
your actual location.
Matta and I used the
upgraded Dauntless.
We were able to extrapolate your location
based on your last known trajectory,
and maybe a little
feminine intuition.
Cadet Zhou has my gratitude,
as do you, Admiral.
Thank you for not
giving up on me.
You're welcome,
but we have a lot we need to discuss.
Please, take a seat.
What can you tell me about
what happened out there?
Unfortunately, very little.
My strike team made it
to the cargo bay safely,
but our attempt to extract
the alien technology
that the courier told us
would be there was interrupted
by Eve Zhou...
Jax's presumed dead mother,
when she appeared
suddenly through a portal.
Suffice it to say that I believe we
were all equally shocked by that.
So,
do you have any idea what the weapon is?
Who developed it? Why
Tierney wants it so badly?
Well,
the "who" is likely the Protector aliens,
the fleet with which
EarthCom tangled last year.
The "what" is that it is some
sort of anti-matter super-weapon.
It literally obliterated every piece of
matter with which it came into contact.
And the "why" is,
that with enough of it,
it could very well
be a planet killer.
You need to find out
more about this weapon,
and whether there are any
more of them out there like it.
Of course, but at this point,
Tierney still seems very able
to cover her tracks
exceedingly well
by using the portals she creates to
transport herself around the galaxy.
Matta may be able
to help us with this.
She's been investigating how
to track my mom and Tierney
by analyzing the energy signatures of
the portals that they've been creating.
Well, if that's possible, then that could
very well be the break we're waiting for.
My thoughts exactly.
Your mission is to follow
that portal wherever it leads,
but more important,
even than arresting Tierney,
is retrieving or eliminating
any more of those weapons.
Understood, Admiral.
Good hunting, Captain.
I actually like what
you've done with the place.
LUCAS: Now is not the time for humor,
Osborn.
I need to find out how
your sister is still alive
- before she's responsible for any more deaths.
- That's impossible, Meredith.
Don't be coy. You
had to have known.
You've been playing us
as fools this whole time,
including your own niece, Jax.
Or is she also a part
of your little deception?
No,
no. If what you're saying is true,
there has to be some reason
she pretended to have been killed
and concealed it from all of us.
This will go down so
much easier for you
if you tell the truth and
stop playing games.
I know there is no love lost between us,
Meredith,
but I am speaking with
complete and utter veracity.
Pity, I don't believe you.
Gentlemen,
take the professor to a holding cell.
Maybe he'll be more forthcoming
after a day or two in solitary.
Meredith,
you're making a grave mistake.
You need to tell me
everything so that I can help you.
I realize this may
come as a shock
to the mighty Donovan Osborn,
but CIS functions quite
ably in your absence.
So, take a good look around.
This might be the last time you'll
be seeing daylight for quite a while.
[♪♪]
You seem to be acclimating
to this new clone body
quicker than I anticipated.
As long as we continue
these treatments,
you should be able
to keep it indefinitely.
As I learned from my
ungrateful progeny,
youth is wasted on the young.
But there are some advantages
of having a young man's body
and an old man's soul.
Now, tell me,
do we have any idea
what the device that destroyed
the freighter actually was?
I've never seen
anything like it.
It appears to be some
kind of anti-matter weapon.
Able to completely consume
solid matter within minutes.
- And what does my daughter Tierney possibly want with it?
- I couldn't say.
Well,
who could've created such a thing?
I couldn't say.
You know absolutely nothing!
Why on earth do I even
keep you in my employ?
I... couldn't say.
If there are more weapons out there,
we must find them.
Imagine having the power
to annihilate entire worlds
and even the stars themselves.
The price they'd fetch on the
open market would be astronomical.
It could change the entire
balance of power in the galaxy.
Continue to monitor our
surveillance on Meredith Lucas.
And if you hear or see anything,
no matter how
inconsequential it may seem,
you will bring it
to me immediately.
And before you go,
get rid of this body.
Find me another before
my next treatment.
[♪♪]
Welcome, Captain Duvall.
Welcome home, Captain.
[CHUCKLES]
- [SIGHS] - Hi.
Hi.
What's wrong?
You know,
I did everything right today,
and it still wasn't enough.
I lost my entire
strike team out there,
and there was nothing
I could do about it.
I saw what happened.
You did everything
that you could.
Maybe I'm not
meant to be captain.
Maybe I can't make the
big life and death decisions.
There's no one I trust more
than you to make those decisions.
What if Lucas was right?
What if when I meant to be
thinking about the mission,
I'm just worrying about you?
If there's one thing
that I know about you,
it's that you always
make the right decision.
Even when it's difficult.
What if the right
decision is wrong?
There's a reason you're
the captain of this boat.
Admiral Lucas trusts you.
Your crew trusts you.
I trust you.
I think you just need
to learn to trust yourself.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
You know, there's one thing I
definitely can't trust myself with.
What's that?
I don't think I can trust myself
to keep my hands off you.
That sounds promising.
- Does it? - Mm-hmm.
- [COMM BEEPS] Captain?
Aud... Um, audio.
Aud... Audio only, please.
Yes, what is it, Ralen?
Matta might finally have
some good news for us.
Great news, terrible timing.
Excuse me, Captain?
I'm on my way.
Sorry.
It's okay.
- Go. - Yeah.
[SIGHS]
You know I'd never let anything
happen to you, Jax... ever.
I know.
See you on the bridge.
Aye-aye, captain, sir.
- Put on a uniform.
- [JAX LAUGHS]
[♪♪]
WOMAN: Warp bubble confirmed.
MAN: Thrusters at 25 percent.
Captain on the bridge.
I have traced the
residual energy signature
from the portal Eve used
to escape the freighter
to a planet in the
Horatius system.
XANDER: Okay. Inhabited?
MATTA: Unknown.
Its location lies outside of Earth'
Defense Perimeter in uncharted space.
Alright. I don't suppose the
Zatarians ever made it out that far?
- Unfortunately, not. - Right.
Well, orders from the admiral
are not open to interpretation.
Our first priority is to find
Tierney and Jax's mother,
and then make sure there are no more
of those anti-matter weapons out there.
I can transmit my
findings to navigation,
but I cannot promise it
will amount to anything.
There's only one way to find out.
Let's follow those breadcrumbs.
Engaging Alcubierre EM drive.
Stabilizing warp bubble and
following the breadcrumbs,
as you ordered, Captain.
[♪♪]
Kubrick for immediate departure.
Aye-aye, Captain.
Let's go find your mother, Jax.
[♪♪]
MATTA: I continue to
detect residual trace readings
from the portal's
energy signature.
Any life signs?
None, but the energy signature
could be interfering
with my scans.
I'd say that's highly likely.
Why is that, Jax?
Well, see for yourself.
That's one of the Ark ships
from the Great
Migration off Earth.
Any chance there
could be survivors?
That ship is over 150 years old.
I'm sure everyone
is long gone by now.
Not quite everyone...
[♪♪]
Whoa. We have a
number of questions,
but firstly,
when are we getting our weapons back?
Given that I'm the one
holding the weapons,
I suggest you let me do
the talking for the moment.
My name is Captain Xander Duvall
of the exploratory vessel,
We come from Earth.
- And as friends.
- These two aren't from Earth.
No. We are Zatarians.
And do you come
as friends as well?
Most assuredly.
Earth and the Zatarians
encountered each other
many years after you
departed on your voyage
to colonize the galaxy.
Aliens from another world.
Never thought I'd see
that with my own eyes.
Our ancestors crashed
here nearly 150 years ago.
Took you long enough to find us.
Actually,
we weren't looking for you.
We were pursuing
dangerous fugitives from Earth.
It's just fortuitous they
led us in your direction.
- What kind of fugitives?
- XANDER: Three women,
wanted by the Earth Confederacy.
One is a criminal.
The other looks exactly like me.
And the third is my mother.
What an interesting
family you have,
but there will be plenty of
time to discuss that later.
On behalf of the
Council of the Elders,
welcome to Clayton's World.
- We don't bow. You...
- What was that?
- We don't... we don't bow.
- Oh.
Thank you.
[SPACECRAFTS FLYING OVERHEAD]
Late night?
My bad. Overslept.
Hey... are we the
only ones here?
What do you think?
I don't get it. What's the
point of having a study group
if there's never a group
here to study with?
It is absolutely infuriating.
Maybe it's time to find
some new study partners?
Uh... okay.
Um, I don't know anyone else,
and I'm struggling
and stressed out
and nobody wants to help.
Have you tried talking to
Jax about how you feel?
Not really. I mean,
she's nice and all,
but she's always
with her boyfriend,
or running off
with the Zatarians.
Yeah. Wish I knew
what their deal was.
I don't know, but what I do know
is I am going to fail Shral's
Advanced Protocol class
if I don't get a lot
more study time in.
Well, let me help.
With my new, advanced,
biotech implants,
I have access to the
entire datastream.
Okay, but you gotta let me
do something for you then.
Do you... like to eat?
- Only food. - [BOTH CHUCKLE]
Let me cook for you,
and we can study over some Garidian Stew.
I am liking the sound of that.
Tonight?
Uh... not tonight.
Unfortunately, I'm, uh...
- previously engaged.
- But the test is tomorrow,
and I'm in class until 1900.
If I get anything less than a "B",
then Shral might drop me
- from the advanced seminar.
- Look, I'm sorry.
I wish I could.
Jett,
the others don't trust you.
I was willing to
give you a pass...
but I guess I was wrong.
Thank you very much.
That has quite a kick to it.
- I like it.
- We ferment it ourselves, obviously.
We call it "Jubjulu".
Everyone we've seen
here is quite young.
Where are all your elderly?
Other than the
Council of Elders?
We thought you were the Council.
We are.
I'm nearly 24 years old.
I can see that you're confused,
but rather than trying to explain it,
it's better that I show you.
Tonight. In the meantime,
though,
allow Tryla to escort you
to your guest chambers.
Well, thank you very much
for your hospitality, Councilor.
And thank you for this delicious
[STAMMERS] chalabalu.
Of course. Our world
is yours to enjoy.
Here we believe
in a life full of fun,
relaxation and
total... pleasure.
Cheers to that. Shall we?
- Matta, if you don't mind...
- Captain Duvall,
if you wouldn't mind
waiting behind a moment.
Thank you.
[CHUCKLES]
[♪♪]
RALEN: There is
something not right here.
You read my mind, Ralen.
I do not trust her.
Perhaps it is because she
shows clear signs of attraction
- towards Captain Duvall.
- I'm not jealous.
I'm just concerned there's
something she's not telling us.
The Councilor did say
they would explain tonight.
I'm not waiting until tonight.
The trail led us here, and I need to see
what I can find out about this planet...
- and my mother.
- Are you sure that's wise?
I don't know if it's wise...
but it's what I'm gonna do.
I am concerned that Jax is
not making rational decisions.
Jax has always been impulsive,
but she understands the mission.
So,
you have nothing to concern yourself with.
Well then,
should I be concerned about you?
Jax is a friend,
and I care deeply for her,
but there's only enough room
in my hearts for you, my love.
When this mission is over,
we will tell them that we're
leaving the Earth for good.
It can't have been
easy for your people
to have been trapped
here alone for...
so many years.
It's the only life
we've ever known.
But, yeah,
it does get boring not meeting anybody new.
And you said that
until we arrived,
your people haven't
had any other visitors?
No.
But it was definitely
worth the wait.
[DISTANT TONE]
What is that?
That would be the sound of all of
your questions about to be answered.
[♪♪]
SHRAL: I must say,
I never expected to see you on
this side of the glass, Donovan.
This is no time for levity.
You need to bloody-well
get me out of here.
I'm being held on some absurd,
trumped-up charges by Lucas.
On the bright side,
at least your sister's still alive.
I understood she
was working with us.
Now I find out she had her
own agenda all along, apparently.
Any idea what her game is?
Eve's already two
steps ahead of us.
The fact that she's working with
Tierney and the other Pandora,
complicates
matters considerably.
Is there anything I can do?
Well, yes, there is one thing.
Get me the hell out of here!
If I knew why Lucas had it out for
you so badly, perhaps I could help.
Oh, it's not important.
It certainly seems important.
The only thing that matters
is stopping the final judgment,
which Lucas
thinks is a fairy tale
I told my people
to keep them in line.
There is a lot more at stake
here than simply my freedom.
I'll talk to her again. I know
you're telling the truth, but...
Do what you can. Don't think
I'll be going anywhere for a while.
- So... - Cheer up, kid.
- Thanks, Martin. - [CHUCKLES]
[♪♪]
Do you see what I'm seeing?
That's a portal.
This must be the portal energy
signature I was detecting, not Eve's.
- What are they doing?
- XANDER: It looks like some sort of festival.
They must imbue the portal
with a cultural or
religious significance.
Welcome to the Departure,
my friends.
Today is not a day to mourn,
but to celebrate.
Though you have outlived
your usefulness to our world,
you'll pass through
to a better one where
- you can grow old peacefully.
- [BOY CRYING] No, Dad, don't go.
No, don't go.
[SOBBING CONTINUES]
[♪♪]
Where did they go?
To a better place, of course.
What better place? I mean,
have you been there?
Nobody has. It's
a one-way ticket.
Then how do you
know it's better?
It's written in
our sacred texts,
handed down by
Nolan "Skip" Clarke,
- the original captain Clayton.
- Whoa.
You must understand our concern
that you're sending citizens off
through a portal that
you know very little about.
We've been through portals
such as these ourselves.
Then you know that they transport
you through space to other worlds.
And we also know that
they can be very dangerous.
You don't understand.
When our Ark ship crashed here,
there were not enough resources
to sustain an entire colony.
So, the decision was made
only the strong would remain.
As soon as you become
a burden to society,
you're sent away.
What do you mean "a burden"?
Surely,
you can appreciate being so young
and beautiful yourselves,
the superiority of
youth. Your strength,
vigor... stamina in
all number of things.
Eventually,
your mind and body will decay.
But with age comes wisdom.
An axiom invented
by an old human male.
Even Einstein's greatest
discoveries were in his early 20s.
So, you're saying that when
one of your number turns 25,
they're sent off
through the portal?
It's what's kept our
colony alive and thriving.
We don't have to care
for our old or infirmed.
Everybody here
is young and vital,
and does not require
anybody to take care of them.
Where I come from,
life is precious at any age.
If you're sending your departed
somewhere they don't even
know where they're departing to,
that's seriously messed up.
From our prior experience,
there's a possibility that
there's no natural resources,
or even oxygen,
through these portals.
They may have just been transported
to the vacuum of space itself.
You are our guests here.
But I will not tolerate
your disrespect
towards our sacred traditions.
Return to your chambers.
In the morning,
I expect you to leave this planet.
- XANDER: What the hell were you thinking?
- JAX: What were you thinking?!
We are on their
planet! We can't just...
Speak up for people who have no voice? They
don't know where they're sending their people.
We're on a mission, Jax!
We need their
cooperation and their help
before we start telling them to
change everything about their society.
There is, in fact,
a certain perverse logic to the practice.
With limited resources,
they could not possibly sustain
a colony of thousands of people
on this world and the
young are more productive.
So, you... you support this?
I do not,
but I understand the rationale behind it.
Right. We are here to find
Tierney and your mother.
- That has to be our priority.
- So, we should just ignore the fact that...
This is extremely odd.
What?
The reading I took of
the portal in the temple
does not correspond to
the reading of the portal
your mom used to
escape the freighter.
So, it was a different
portal that brought us here.
And if this is true, then Tierney and
Eve could still be on the planet after all.
If my readings are correct,
that is more than possible.
- Okay. - Where are you going?
- I'm going to confront Jennifer.
- I'm coming with you.
No. You're staying
right here with the others.
Is that an order?
What do you think?
So you agree with your friend?
She's not my friend.
She's a member of my crew.
That's not what I asked.
Have we really been
away from Earth so long
that we seem that
different to you?
Maybe you'll understand
when you return to Earth.
But we're not going
to return to Earth.
This is our home.
Why would we ever leave?
It's the only life
we've ever known.
[♪♪]
RALEN: I don't know.
We need to see
that portal again.
You may recall that the captain
gave us strict orders
to remain here.
I must have missed that.
You coming or what?
ZAZIE: Jett? Are you in there?
Jett!
Computer, locate Jett Annamali.
[♪♪]
Jax told me not to trust you,
and obviously she was right.
What are you doing here, Zazie?
I was coming to apologize
for the way that I acted today,
but now I see your hot date was
with Professor Shral's file cabinet.
- Wait...
- To steal the test, I presume?
[SCOFFS]
You need to stay out of my business,
Zazie.
And you need to
steer clear of Shral.
Either you tell Professor Shral
what you've been up to, or I will.
- [SIGHS] - [DOOR CLOSES]
[♪♪]
[ELECTRICAL ZAPPING]
[DEVICE BEEPING]
This portal is
entirely unstable.
Well... aren't all portals
inherently unstable?
Portals are miniature wormholes,
and for the duration in
which they are triggered,
they are temporarily stable.
This one, however,
seems to be permanently
malfunctioning.
Could it have been damaged
when the Ark ship crashed here?
I will need more data to support that
hypothesis, but... it is highly likely.
Let's find out for sure.
[DRONE BEEPS]
What just happened?
The drone was destroyed.
This is not an active portal.
That means that the Council has
been putting their own people to death
for over a hundred years.
Yes.
That's exactly what it means.
How could they not tell their
own people of the danger?
JAX: I'm not sure yet.
We need to find
the original Clayton.
It might help us find
what we're looking for.
[BELL RINGS]
- [KNOCKING] - Come in.
I'm sorry to bother you,
Professor.
I know you're,
like... super busy.
Indeed, I am. So,
please, be brief.
I don't want to be a snitch,
but Jett snuck into
your office last night
to steal the questions for
today's exam. I caught him.
- So...?
- So, what are you gonna do about it?
I'm going to do nothing.
Good day, Cadet Nichols.
Look, I know Jett's getting a
second chance here at the Academy,
but you can't just overlook the
fact that he's a liar and a cheat.
Actually, I can.
Perhaps this is
something better discussed
with Jett himself, Cadet.
[SCOFFS]
[♪♪]
Mind if I join you?
Jax, what are you doing here?
I asked you to stay outside.
You know the truth
about the portal.
You've known this entire time,
haven't you?
What are you talking about?
It kills everyone
that goes through it.
The Departure takes
our elder citizens
to a better place they can live
out the rest of their lives in peace.
She's lying.
The portal's unstable.
It actually doesn't go anywhere,
and I can prove it.
I downloaded the
manifest Clayton.
Jennifer Clarke was
the 24-year-old daughter
of the captain Clayton.
Look familiar?
But she hasn't aged a day
since they crashed here.
Why is that?
Because without the unique
energy of the malfunctioning portal,
Jennifer would have been
dead over a hundred years ago.
That's why she can't
leave this planet.
The Council of Elders has
been leeching off this portal
this entire time in
order to stay alive.
The Council of Elders,
you're all the original colonists.
They're all original
crew Clayton.
Everyone else here is
just their descendants.
We did what we had to do.
How could you do that
to your own people?
It's called survival.
BOTH: It's called murder.
And as citizens of the Earth Confederacy,
you are all under arrest.
EVE: No, I don't think so.
[♪♪]
Hello...
daughter.
[♪♪]
- I have so many questions for you.
- I'm sure you do.
Right now, I just need to know
what's gonna happen to my friends.
I don't have any control over that,
Jax.
Well, we need to do something.
'Cause if we don't
Jennifer is going to kill them.
- I suspect you're correct.
- JAX: That's it?
That's all you have to say?
You let me think that you
were dead for over a year,
and that's all you have
to say to me right now?
And Dad? What about him?
Your father is dead.
I'm sorry.
I tried to save him,
but I couldn't.
I don't even know
who you are anymore.
Yes,
you do. You know exactly who I am,
- and you need to trust me.
- Trust you?
You're working with Tierney
and the other Pandora.
How in the worlds am I
supposed to trust you?
- Ask me anything. I'll give you the absolute truth.
- Why are you here?
To observe the
malfunctioning portal.
So you knew that
it was unstable.
You knew that anyone who
passed through it would die,
and you didn't do
a thing to stop that!
What I knew is if I supplied
rations and supplies to the Council
they would let me continue
to pursue my mission.
Which is what exactly?
Why is that broken
portal so important to you?
[SCOFFS]
Because we know of no
other portal in the galaxy
that has been
permanently disabled.
[SCOFFS]
Did you ever even love me?
- EVE: Of course.
-'Cause it really doesn't feel like you did.
- Of course, I did. - You "did"?
I do. It's just that sometimes,
Jax,
there are obligations that
are more important than family.
No.
Family should always come first.
It doesn't work that way.
One day you'll understand.
But until then,
know that I did...
I do
and I will always love you.
And Tierney?
Why is she so important to you?
When I was younger,
I had a relationship with
my brother's best friend...
against my better judgment.
Harlan Fried.
Sadly, he could be very
charming when he wanted to be.
So,
Tierney is also your daughter?
Yes.
So...
you and she are sort of...
sisters.
What are you gonna
do with my crew?
They'll be sent through the portal,
of course.
You know that I'm not
gonna be able to allow that.
JENNIFER: I didn't think so.
But you know our secret...
I suppose I could
spare just one life...
if you agree to
stay here with me.
Yeah. That's so
not going to happen.
Well...
let's not drag this
out any longer then.
It's time for you all to experience
the Departure for yourselves
and go to a better
place... forever.
[♪♪]
You have reached
the Age of Departure.
It's not a day to mourn,
but to celebrate.
Though you have outlived
your usefulness in our world...
You can spare us the ritual,
thank you.
I think we all know
how this is going to end.
Jennifer,
let me take my daughter with me.
She won't say anything,
I promise.
You can do what you
want with the others.
JENNIFER: I admire
your compassion for Jax,
but the Council are not
willing to take that risk.
[♪♪]
[ALL GRUNTING]
Enough!
[WEAPON BEEPS]
How is there two of you?
Long story.
Why did you help save us?
I asked her to.
And I wanted you to see
this pathetic world, Jax.
Proof of the
unworthiness of mankind.
They murdered their own people
in order to preserve their youth.
This is the universe
you're so desperate to save.
Why are you really here, Mom?
I told you, to study the portal.
A broken portal? Why?
Because as long as the portals exist,
there's a way for this universe to be saved.
A way for you to
reach the Ancients.
- If she destroys it, then there will be no...
- Hope.
You're not going to win.
I'll find the Ancients, and convince
them that this universe is worth sparing.
I'm afraid that's not possible,
Jax.
You've already told them this
universe isn't worth saving, didn't you?
The destruction of this
universe has already begun,
and without the
portals to reach them,
there's nothing
you can do to stop it.
[MUSICAL INTRODUCTION ON P.A.]
Join us...
Jett. Hey, wait up.
I need to get to class.
So, I spoke to Professor Shral,
and he didn't seem
to care what you did.
But I do.
You need to tell me
what's going on with you.
You need to stop messing with my life,
okay?
Just leave me alone.
Is that really what you want,
for no one to care about you?
You wouldn't understand, Zazie.
I know what it's like to be
forced into making bad choices.
Trust me.
Okay.
Join us for a very
special lecture...
Look, after getting in trouble
last semester for sending...
everybody those holo-nudes of Pilar,
I...
I didn't like the
person I'd become.
I don't blame you. I
wouldn't have liked him either.
And I paid the price.
I didn't just get suspended.
I lost my entire scholarship.
So,
my family doesn't have money.
So...
I'm working night shifts
at the Academy as a...
[WHISPERS] ...janitor
to pay my tuition.
That's what you were doing
in Professor Shral's office,
cleaning it?
Yeah.
Oh, my God! That is so great!
- That's so great!
- What's great about it?
I thought you were a
thief and a liar and a cheat.
Okay, maybe you missed what I said,
I'm a... janitor.
So what? It's honest, hard work.
I know what you're
going through.
Screw these rich,
privileged kids.
You and I,
we gotta to stick together.
- [LAUGHS] - Come on.
Let's "jet" to class.
JETT: "Jet to class"? Really?
JAX: You have to undo
whatever you told the Ancients.
Humanity is worth saving.
JAX 2: I observed this universe
and made my
decision 22 years ago.
Nothing has changed.
You haven't seen the
good in people like I have.
Let me show you.
I saw everything I needed to see
when Osborn put me in that box.
Do you know what that was like?
The darkness. The loneliness.
The dreams. The nightmares.
They were only doing what
they thought they had to do.
And they were wrong,
and I am so sorry.
We can go to the
Ancients together
to stop the final judgment.
No one has to die.
JAX 2: My decision
has been made.
Then I'll go to them myself.
Get away from her!
Xander, no!
[SHOUTING]
[GASPING]
- Jax? - What have you done?
Jax, she was gonna kill you.
[♪♪]
MAN: Thank you,
Captain Duvall. Good luck to you.
WOMAN: Thank you, Captain.
MAN 2: Thank you
for everything you did.
Right. All the colonists all
know what happened now.
Will they return
back to Earth with us?
No. No. They have
decided to stay here.
Forge a new life and
grow old together.
And the Council of Elders?
They will be delivered to
EarthCom and stand trial.
We need to ensure
that the remaining colonists
receive the proper provisions
and supplies necessary to
create a functioning society.
Of course, Captain.
Your doppelganger was wrong,
Jax.
When we see something that's broken,
we fix it.
That's what makes us human.
No, Xander.
Not everything that's
broken can be fixed.
[♪♪]
EVE: She'll never
forgive you for this.
Your love for my daughter
will be the end of you...
or her.
Either way,
you've made things worse.
I would do anything
to protect Jax.
Yes. That's the problem.
We have surrounded
the brig with a forcefield
even Tierney will not be
able to penetrate with a portal.
You're not going anywhere.
That's quite all right, Ralen.
I'm exactly where I want to be.
I did the right thing,
Ralen, didn't I?
Killing the other Jax?
If you had not
done what you did,
I most certainly would
have done the same.
Thank you.
I think I needed to hear that.
[ELECTRICITY SIZZLES]
Ooh. [CHUCKLES]
[BEEPING]
XANDER: Jax?
Jax. Can you open the door,
please?
Can we talk?
[BEEPING]
Jax?
Captain Duvall,
please report to the bridge immediately.
[SIGHS]
I'm on my way.
[♪♪]
Captain, we are receiving
a universal distress call
from the Zatarian warship
N'Kantu.
I've seen this before.
[♪♪]
They are gone.
- XANDER: Red alert!
- [ALARM BLARES]
I am calculating the trajectory
of the wave of destruction.
It will continue straight
through the sector
on a direct route towards...
Zatar.
[♪♪]
Kill, Ubu, kill.
Good fish.
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org