♪ Day-oh! ♪
AUDIENCE: ♪ Day-oh! ♪
D'oh!
AUDIENCE: ♪ D'oh! ♪
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.addic7ed.com
- (horns honking)
- Come on, out of my way!
Where was this traffic when
I was driving to church?
- (horn honks)
- Homie, calm down.
We're not going to miss the
San Castellaneta Festival.
I love San Castellaneta.
Delicious food, wonderful people.
It's just like being in Italy.
But with streets that are wide
enough I can fit in them.
(sucks on pacifier)
And I love the rides that are dangerous
because they're 100 years old.
(people groaning)
(country music playing)
(carnival music playing)
Hold on, kids. Here we go.
(chains clinking)
I beat out a mule and
an ox for this job.
The secret is not to ask for benefits.
♪ Give me pizza, give me pasta ♪
♪ Give me lots of cannoli ♪
♪ I'll drink sambuca till I puke-a ♪
♪ Then I'll finish with spumoni ♪
♪ Drink until my legs are Jell-O ♪
♪ Cheap red wine and limoncello... ♪
(grunting)
(laughter)
(vocalizing)
(Homer humming outside)
You want us to bring you anything back
from the festival, Tone?
No. It's all carbs.
I don't want people to think I'm fat.
But your name is Fat Tony.
It blends.
I can't believe you're not going,
after I flew out your uncle from Sicily.
- Idiota!
- That icy glare
is why I left the old country.
Tightlips, you do a poor
job of reading my moods.
But you're the only one I trust.
Go. Enjoy your festival
while I sit here bonding with my uncle.
Do you want to go to the festival, zio?
(scoffs, spits loudly)
I came to this country
for the Burning Man.
Before I die,
I want to see a naked crunchy
chick riding a bicycle.
♪ Everybody has a treat... ♪
- (grunts)
- (people gasp)
- Opa!
- That's Greek, Chief.
Hey, Lou, when's the festival
for Saint Know-It-All?
- Uh, I believe it's October the...
- There isn't one!
Nobody likes a know-it-all. Idiot.
Hey, we got a-zeppole,
we got a-braciole,
capicola, scungilli,
and I don't know what
the hell-a this is.
Can you make it all in
one thing and fry it?
I saw-a you coming.
Ooh. This place looks interesting.
Dad, no, that's an actual church.
(shrieks)
Welcome, everyone, to this festival
that does not celebrate
Christopher Columbus.
Repeat: not Columbus.
As we stand here at the corner
of Niña and Pinta and Santa Maria,
let us welcome your
master of cere-spumonies,
Aquaman himself,
Jason Morororora.
(fanfare plays)
It is an honor to be here on land today
to recount the inspiring
story of this great saint.
- Aquaman.
- Sign my left boob. (grunts)
Aquaman is not here for
the signing of boobs.
That's a separate event at the
Marriott. Conference room C.
(conch blows)
In 250 A.D., Brother
Ignatius Castellaneta
refused to recant his Christian faith.
And so the Romans chopped off his head,
they chopped off his arms,
they chopped off his legs, and
they chopped off his toes.
They shot him with arrows
made of frozen snakes
and they pulled out his
eyes and replaced them
with chocolate-covered pistachios.
But still, Ignatius refused to recant.
So they boiled his bones
in sparkling cherry wine.
So that's why the thrice-martyred saint
is remembered with spumoni,
the chocolate pistachio
cherry ice cream treat.
(retches) Ugh. Not good.
Uh, yes, uh, thank you, Super-Fish.
And now, let us show our
deep reverence for Jesus
by festooning his statue
with dollar bills.
♪ ♪
Pin a dollar on Jesus, Homer.
He doesn't need money.
(whispers): I hear his father's loaded.
(Marge groans)
Hey, where's my wallet?
Yeah, my wallet's gone, too.
- My purse!
- My belt!
My clutch!
We are the victims of a
pocket-picking pandemic.
Do something, Wet Panther!
♪ ♪
Peter Piper picked a
peck of pocket wallets?
How many paupers did Peter's
pocket picking produce?
(sighs) I'm afraid no pants are
safe from this Dockers stalker,
this chino bandito,
this trouser browser.
But Chief Wiggum vows he will
solve this pickle of a puzzle.
Oh, I solved it, all right.
"Thief of polite." "Thief of polite."
I said it first!
Wiggum, I hate to interrupt
this important police work...
"Police." That's it. "Thief of police."
Hey! I need that to switch
to Access Hollywood.
You need a lot more than that.
I'm Lenora Carter, special investigator
from the attorney general's office,
and I'm taking over this case.
Uh, look, ma'am, you
seem nice, but no one
comes into my precinct
and tells me what to do.
- Shut up and listen.
- Yes, ma'am.
You are the worst police officer
I've ever had the pleasure
of humiliating in front of his men.
(chuckles) You are so fat,
you're good cop and bad cop.
Your drug-sniffing dog is in rehab.
Okay, it's for sex addiction.
You there, Riggs and Murtaugh. Ha.
- Hmm.
- O-Oh.
It's time to do some real police work.
I see, fine. No, go ahead.
I'll go work out my
feelings on the gun range.
(gunfire)
We don't have a gun range!
- (gunfire)
- (Wiggum screams)
We'll trap the pickpocket by
planting a wallet with a tracer
in a rear end so huge, no
criminal could miss it.
We need to find the biggest ass in town.
HOMER: Hello.
Could you direct me to the
Office of Park Bench Removal?
Yeah, just take a seat, sir.
Thank you, I have my own.
(vocalizing)
I'm not letting my
husband risk his life.
I admit it, I'm scared.
Ma'am, this is a matter
of public urgency.
Your husband's rear end is
bigger than the both of us.
(laughs)
(humming)
With your kids' permission, we can watch
your father's butt crack
this case wide open.
(Bart and Lisa laugh)
(chuckles)
"Wide open."
Homer, we're placing this
tracking device in your wallet.
Then you just have to put that
sweet seat meat on the street.
Now let me pull your wallet up
so it's just peeking over the pocket.
Uhp-bup-bup. Allow me.
Pick a card. Any card.
Thank God that thing is on our side.
♪ I don't think you're ready for this ♪
♪ 'Cause my body's too
bootylicious for you, babe... ♪
(audience booing)
♪ I don't think you're
ready for this jelly ♪
♪ I don't think you're ready for this ♪
♪ 'Cause my body's too
bootylicious for you, babe ♪
♪ Baby, can you handle this? ♪
(whoops)
- (beeping)
- We've got our target.
(quietly): What are you doing here?
(quietly): I admit it,
I couldn't stay away.
I was following you.
Also, I was driving around
to put Ralphie to sleep.
That kid will not go down.
I'm a lotto ball. You lose again, Daddy.
We're going in.
Ah-ah-ah. Except you.
♪ ♪
(gunshot echoes)
Ah, you work with two guys all your life
and you think you know 'em.
Betrayed by Lou and, uh, the other guy.
What is his name again?
(chuckles): I-I want to say Greg.
You know, Uncle, guests, like
fish, stink after three days.
I told you once, I told
you a thousand times,
I'm not leaving until
my wife forgives me.
- She's dead.
- You always take her side!
Cops? What are you doing here?
This is a setup. W-What
are these things?
I was told this was an Asian
fusion pop-up restaurant,
but I see no Asian nor fusion.
Marion "Fat Tony" D'Amico,
you're under arrest for
heading a pickpocket ring.
But I've never seen
these wallets before.
The-the room is spinning.
So this is what it feels
like to be innocent.
(body thuds)
And this is how it feels
to be irrelevant.
Daddy's an elephant.
No-no, I'm not an elephant, Ralphie,
and-and please don't you forget it.
("Baby Elephant Walk" by
Henry Mancini playing)
The Wolf of Wallet Street? (chuckles)
Reputed mobster Fat Tony D'Amico
is at last behind bars.
My wife.
My goomar.
My teacup pig.
(pig squeals)
(Wiggum groans)
What's wrong, Chief?
Marge, you ever felt like
life has passed you by,
there's no point?
Oh, you're just having a rough patch.
It happens to all men in their 50s.
I'm 38, Marge.
(Marge groans)
Chief, do you know why
I love my husband?
For that most romantic
of reasons: inertia.
I love him because he's
not afraid to fail.
He has boundless unjustified
confidence, and you should, too.
Really? You think so?
Boy, suddenly, I-I see
a break in the clouds.
I will not let you down, Marge.
Uh, Marge, can I get a
ride to the station?
Uh, Ralphie will stay with the car.
♪ ♪
Dear Lord, who sees all, the
jabronis and the mamalukes,
you know I am innocent.
In your mercy and by your grace,
help me kneecap the rat
Judas who set me up.
Amen.
Almighty God, I'm not a praying man.
For me, getting down on my
knees is often a one-way trip.
I-I know I made a deal with
the devil to be chief,
but please just ignore that
and help me out, will ya?
Dear Lord, please bring
back plastic straws.
The paper ones get soggy so fast.
I brought the mob lawyer right
away like you asked, boss.
They wouldn't even let
me put my pants on.
I was barely able to grab my rate clock.
Al diavolo rate clock.
Get me out of here.
- And I mean fast.
- Patience. Patience.
Okay, what have they got you on?
(slowly): Murder one?
(slowly): Murder two?
Pickpocketing! Quit talking slow!
(slowly): All right.
Actually, I'm innocent.
Innocent?! Innocent?!
A judge wouldn't believe
you for a second.
I've got nothing to work with here.
What would you even plead?
You really did it this time.
- I didn't do it.
- (groans)
- You want me to whack him, boss?
- No! Just usher him out.
Got it. I'll "usher him out."
I mean show him the door.
Right. I'll "show him the door."
Whatever you think I want you
to do, just do the opposite!
(muttering in Italian)
(speaking Italian)
(both speaking Italian)
_
♪ ♪
The one crime I would never
commit is pickpocketing.
Huh. He seems sincere.
I am sincere.
When I was a boy, my
father, Fatso Antonio,
needed a heart transplant.
On its way to the hospital,
that heart was pickpocketed.
My father died the way
no made man should die:
of natural causes.
(cries)
Oh, my God. I discovered a clue.
(chuckles) I found an
electric toothbrush.
(Taser crackles)
Well, he'll sleep good tonight.
I can tell he's innocent,
with a certainty you can only develop
putting hundreds of
innocent people in jail.
DNA technology has not been my friend.
GUARD: Lights out!
Psst. Psst, psst.
Why do you "psst" me?
I'm not going anywhere.
(quietly): I think you're innocent.
But you're gonna have to convince me
to ignore your entire past history.
♪ ♪
I was not born a rich man.
Where I grew up, there was
one way out: your fists.
Or the many scholarships available
to young Italian-American students.
But the forms required information,
and I ain't no snitch.
All right, I'm losing my confidence.
You did it, didn't you?
I swear on this former
priest that I didn't do it.
He's not guilty.
- And I know guilty.
- And I can prove it.
- Well, go ahead.
- I said I can prove it.
I didn't say I would.
Well, why wouldn't you?
Because what I was actually
doing at the time is something
a mob boss cannot do
and let people know.
If you help me, I swear an oath
we'll find the guy that framed you.
All right, I will show
you what I was doing
when the heist went down.
(groans): Oh.
It's so embarrassing, it has to be true.
Give me your phone.
This is what I do every
day at that time,
the time of the crime.
As you will see, I walk
into my private space,
I gargle,
and then, God help me, I...
- ♪ Good times and bum times ♪
- ("I'm Still Here" playing)
♪ I've seen them all and, my dear ♪
♪ I'm still here ♪
♪ Plush velvet sometimes ♪
♪ Sometimes just pretzels and beer ♪
(grunts)
♪ But I'm here... ♪
Now you know. When I'm
alone, I sing show tunes.
You didn't steal those
wallets. You stole my heart.
Leave it on.
♪ Ten years a mob boss,
hits and whacks ♪
♪ Bought judges and mayors,
and never paid tax... ♪
- Okay, that's enough.
- (music stops)
Definitely enough.
We're gonna get you out, today.
(groans)
Appreciate the offer, Chief,
but prison has changed me.
Now I'm thinking I should just
give up, serve out my term,
then sit in the warm sun
outside the butcher shop.
Isn't that what you always did?
Yeah, but every few hours,
someone would whisper
something into my ear,
then I had to decide
whether to nod or shrug.
It was very stressful. The agita.
Uh, I thought you wanted to
get the guy who put you here.
I do.
Well, we will, if you will wear a wire.
I'm sorry, but on principle,
that is something I cannot do.
Let me repeat: something I cannot do.
♪ ♪
(tires screech)
Now, remember the phrase
to call for help.
- What phrase?
- "Remember the phrase."
I will. What phrase is it?
"Remember the phrase."
I would if you would tell me what it is.
The phrase is "remember the phrase."
That is the dumbest
thing I've ever heard.
Just remember, your life depends on us.
Oh, and please, no profanity.
I play these for the missus
when we're, uh, we're
getting in the mood.
(laughs)
(groans)
A toast to Fat Tony, a man
like a Botticelli nude:
fat, old and easy to frame, huh?
(laughter)
Hello, fellas.
Fat Tony. I was just saying
how much we missed you.
Huh? Huh, guys?
- Oh, yeah, sure. Yeah, we said that.
- (nervous murmuring)
Quiet! I don't want to hear anybody
but Frankie the Squealer.
W-W-What do, w-what do you
want to hear from me?
The name of the man who
framed you? I would never.
I didn't say Johnny Tightlips.
I would never say Johnny Tightlips.
Ladies and gentlemen, our
new boss, Johnny Tightlips.
So, it was you, Johnny.
- What? Hey! Whoa!
- You!
After all your
passive-aggressive replies
and bitter looks, I
never would've guessed.
You mistook my taciturn
nature for fealty.
But it was simply that I
didn't feel comfortable
in social situations.
Then I saw this commercial
where a sad cloud goes
on a date with the sun.
So I talked to my doctor about Paxil,
and it gave me the
confidence to betray you.
(agreeable chatter)
This is my crew now. Ain't
that right, Jimmy Kissass?
You was always my favorite.
What about you, Sonny Go-along?
I'm good if everyone else is.
- Willie Whatever?
- Whatever.
And you, Joey Can't-Read-the-Room?
You're nuts! Ain't none of
us gonna go along with this!
Yeah, see, that's... You
didn't... that's not...
(bottle shatters)
("Don't Stop Believin'"
by Journey playing)
♪ Just a small town girl... ♪
I'm surprised Maggie isn't here.
♪ Lonely world ♪
♪ She took the midnight train ♪
♪ Going anywhere... ♪
Mmm, this pasta's delicious.
I'm gonna find out what the sauce is.
Remember the phrase.
WIGGUM (over radio):
Remember what phrase?
- Oh, right.
- (siren wailing)
Ooh, sauce.
Oh! I'm hit!
Right in the heart... of your ass.
Someone's got to suck out the bullet.
Wiggum, damn it, this is
what you were born to do.
(sucking)
- ♪ Don't stop... ♪
- (music stops abruptly)
There he is.
We thought we were gonna lose
you for a minute there, champ.
(laughs)
You have the chief here to thank.
His quick suction may
have saved your life.
(hoarse): Thank you.
Well, Wiggum, I have to say,
when I first met you,
I thought you were totally incompetent.
(chuckles)
And?
- And?
- (tires screech)
And?! A-And?! And?!
I believe in you, Chief.
And, yeah, that-that's enough.
The three of us, we are
not that different.
Whoa! Hey, whoa!
What's this guy talking about?
We are cicciobomba,
who like to sit in the sun
and enjoy a nice prosciutto.
Cicciobomba, prosciutto.
You guys make garbage sound good.
We call garbage spazzatura.
Mmm... garbage.
- (laughter)
- Garbage.
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.addic7ed.com