- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
What, too soon?
(EXCLAIMS)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
(BELCHES)
(WORK WHISTLE BLOWS)
Aah!
(SCANNER BEEPS)
(TIRES SCREECH)
D'oh!
(GRUNTS)
Avast there.
It be too late to alter course, matey.
And there be pirates
lurking in every cove.
Get to the ride.
(ALL SCREAMING)
Did they get a picture?
Welcome to our first-ever
night of dramatic scenes
written by our students.
Should we silence our
cell phones and pagers?
No, no, no, please,
I beg you, leave them on.
An-And here-here's some candy to unwrap.
(AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING)
And now, an new scene
from the CW's Riverdale.
(STUDENTS CHEER)
Jughead, there's been a murder
at Pop's Chock'lit Shoppe
and it's up to us kids to solve it.
I can't deal with that right now.
My dad's in jail and the
only way to get him out
is to try drugs.
We're both pregnant
with Big Moose's babies.
Wait. So this is a play
based on a YouTube
of kids playing a video game?
- That's right.
- (SCOFFS) It's about time.
Okay, to get their chug jugs,
I could snipe these guys out one by one,
but the smarter move
is to plant a charge
at the base of their attack platform
and skull-splat 'em when they land.
Hey, guys, if you want
more game hacks like this,
be sure to smash our like button
and subscribe to our channel.
Up next, night vision fails.
How is this a play?
Well, sir, video game walk-throughs
are the only narrative
most of these kids
have been exposed to.
- This is their Becket.
- BOTH: Who?
Are you Terry Bradshaw?
No. It's, uh, Donny Osmond.
Boner. Boner from Growing Pains.
(DISTORTED): You're all
wrong. My real identity is...
Flavor Flav!
Flavor Flav? I've heard of you.
I've heard of you so much.
I am such a huge fan of your
movies, books, or music.
I can also pretend to be impressed.
ALL: The end.
(SCATTERED APPLAUSE)
Wake up. Lisa's next.
Oh, no, please. I'm
having the best dream.
I was in my warm, cozy grave.
Well, I'm gonna dream about
me in a soft, cuddly crypt.
- Yeah...
- Ah...
Amazingly, this next piece
is not based on something
you watch on your phone or a gas pump,
but is actually an
honest-to-goodness play,
by Lisa "Thank God You're
a Throwback" Simpson.
And so I give you
Long Day's Journey Into Light Beer.
Where's my beer, Marjorie?
I spent all day making
sure this beer was cold.
Aah! I make bad choices.
Lisa's really nailed the Hibberts.
(CHUCKLES)
Uh, yo, dude, my catchphrases
are as outdated as my slingshot.
Ay, caramba!
Oh, Mom, it's so hard being
a straight-A student
with a social conscience
who writes amazing plays.
The only stable thing
in this house is you,
making every day the same as the last.
Exactly the same.
Like the coffee maker says,
things will perk up.
I thought you were the coffee maker.
You can learn a lot from percolators.
Make the most of the daily grind.
The mother character is such a snooze.
Ralph has nothing to play against.
(GASPS) They think I'm boring.
(GASPS) This play is about us!
Today I decided to be a race car driver,
so I was, then I quit.
I also have exciting news.
I converted four soap slivers
into practically a new bar.
Is this how the world sees me... as a...
How do the kids say lame-o these days?
We say lame-o, you lame-o.
Suck, suck. And I felt like the ghost
belonging to the fog.
And the fog was the ghost of the sea.
Suck, suck.
(CHEERING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
You really think I'm that boring?
Lisa, you made someone feel sad,
which is not what a drama about
a family is supposed to do.
Marge, could we get a picture?
Okay.
- (YAWNS)
- (SHUTTER CLICKS)
_
So all the generations...
Boring. They think I'm boring.
I'll show them who's boring.
Now, this morning, Marge Simpson
has insistently volunteered
to read a passage.
She says she's gonna
bring her own spin to it.
(HUMMING A TUNE)
Now, a reading from John, 18:38,
between Pontius Pilate and Jesus.
(QUIETLY): Marge! Marge! Marge!
(EXAGGERATED ITALIAN
ACCENT): Hey-a Jesus,
what's a matter for you?
You saying youse a king?
(NORMAL VOICE) He was Roman,
that's why I'm doing the accent.
(MAN COUGHS)
Anyhoo, Jesus answered,
and I think it might have gone
something like this.
(IMITATING JACKIE MASON):
I'm not a king, I'm a carpenter.
A Jewish carpenter.
The only thing I nail are my SATs.
So then, Pontius says to the elders,
"This-a Jesus, he-a
look like a nice-a guy."
Nobody talk-a like-a that.
I make a nice-a sentence.
Just like-a Mama used to construct.
- Oh...
- Can we just hear
Lovejoy's sermon, please?
Yeah, Marge, read the room.
Mm...
You need this more than we do, lady.
Boring. That's what this
straight-A Girl Scout
has become... boring.
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(SCREAMING)
(GASPS) You just had a
near-death experience.
That's exciting.
Whoo! What a rich life you lead, Mom.
I'm going to bed.
That will really turn around
your boring reputation.
Shh.
(GRUNTING)
(SNORING)
(SIGHS) Don't worry,
Homer, I'll chop the wood.
Like always.
I have to do everything. (GRUNTS)
Even chop the trees.
(GRUNTING)
- Hyah!
- Whoa!
- (CHUCKLES)
Hyah!
Mmm. I know where she can put
that chopping to good use.
- Homer's neck?
- No.
He doesn't have one. Something better.
Lower your right hand.
Gives you more power.
Hmm.
Thanks, um...
Paula. Friend of Patty's.
We met at Burning Woman.
Nice job on that wood.
HOMER (WEAKLY): I helped.
Yeah, you helped, all right.
You helped that hammock kiss the ground.
(WEAKLY): D'oh.
Marge, I don't know if you know this,
but I'm a top-level
contender at Timbersports.
That's so interesting.
How does it feel to be magnificent?
I'll show you.
♪ The only card I need
is the ace of spades ♪
♪ The ace of spades. ♪
(CHAIN SAW BUZZING)
That is a fascinating hobby.
(SIGHS) Timbersports
is more than a hobby.
It's an unpaid passion that
you do in your spare time.
Now, we're going to the woods.
(BREATHES DEEPLY) Ah.
- What are you doing?
- Breathing.
Breathing for the first time in my life.
Ah.
Can I do one thing
for the knots in your shoulders?
Sure.
Aah... Ooh, ooh! Ooh!
Not so... Oh.
Now, to motivate your chopping,
think of things that make you mad.
Oh, nothing really makes me mad.
Mom, Lisa won't stay on her
side of the thought bubble.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
You have five seconds to live. (GRUNTS)
So do you, idiot. We're
in the same bubble.
My final words are Lisa sucks!
(GRUNTING)
She's a natural.
♪ ♪
♪ I walked into the forest ♪
♪ So beautiful and green ♪
♪ And there I saw a woman ♪
♪ Who was chopping down a tree ♪
♪ The sawdust was flyin' ♪
♪ She was spinnin' on a log ♪
♪ On her waist was
strapped a tool belt ♪
♪ With a Black & Decker saw ♪
♪ Vroom, vroom, pull the cord ♪
♪ Buzz, buzz, just one more ♪
♪ Roar, roar, what a thrill ♪
♪ With Lumberjill ♪
♪ Vroom, vroom, pull the cord ♪
♪ Buzz, buzz, just one more ♪
♪ Roar, roar, what a thrill ♪
♪ With Lumberjill. ♪
Ooh, ooh...
_
I'm Chip Bunyan, eh, and welcome
to the Springfield Timbersports Pro-Am.
I'm here with former NBA
analyst Anger Watkins.
Timbersports. Timber sports?
I snap one P.A.'s bra strap,
and this is where I land?
Who is the Lebron of this
thing? No one will tell me.
His name is Matt Cogar.
Is his nickname The Cougar?
No, his nickname is Matt.
Matt isn't a nickname.
It's a name name.
(STAMMERS) I'd storm
out of here right now
if I weren't so terrified of squirrels.
Take my money! Take it!
I'm glad Mom's found a passion,
but I wish she didn't have
to kill all those trees.
I read that trees are the
cause of global warming.
Where'd you read that?
My new fourth grade science book.
(GRUMBLES)
(WHISTLES)
(ALL GRUNTING)
And they're off, displaying
lots of forest gumption, eh?
First we have Nelson Muntz.
He's ten years old, but,
man, is it a hard ten.
(GRUNTING)
(SLURRING): Hey. That's my boy.
He gets his pole skills from his mama.
Oh! Marge Simpson takes the lead!
No one saw this coming,
because no one was watching.
(STAMMERS) What could
possibly be her motivation?
I'm not boring!
(GROWLS)
- Woo-hoo!
- Yay!
You magnificent she-beast.
All our sweaty passion
and grunting paid off.
Now's the time I should tell you.
Paula is gay.
Aw. She made a friend.
You've made me a new woman.
Oh. Should I be concerned?
It's no weirder than that time
our knees touched under the bar.
You still think about that?
Every day.
(HUMMING A TUNE)
Aw. I haven't been this
happy in a long time.
You were great, but I have a question.
Do you want to take
it to the next level?
What do you mean?
Will you ride the blade with me?
You know, help me bow
the jagged-toothed fiddle?
I don't understand.
Draw and drag the sequoia widow-maker.
You're gonna have to tell me
what you're talking about.
Will you be my partner on
the double-ended bucksaw?
You really think that
I have what it takes?
I know you do.
But if we do this,
you'll have to train with me
for a month, in Portland.
A month? Oh, no, I can't
leave Homer that long.
♪ ♪
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(SCREAMING)
_
Oh. Fantasies can be good?
(HUMMING A TUNE)
Good to have you back.
(HUMMING)
(YAWNS) Boy, am I beat.
Homie, I feel like
I'm my very best self
in these competitions.
You are, honey.
In a way I could never make
you feel or comprehend.
Paula wants me to train with her.
If I do, I'll be gone for a month.
A month? We've never
been apart that long.
I miss you when we're
separated in a revolving door.
I miss you when I'm putting
a sweater over my head.
I miss you when I close
my eyes during a sneeze.
I miss you when the clock
springs ahead an hour.
We'll never get that time back.
Homer, do you really want me to stay,
knowing how much I need this
to feel good about myself?
Yes, I do.
- (GRUMBLES)
- What? What?
Where you going?
She might leave and never come back.
Just like the McRib.
(CRYING)
_
- _
- ♪ You feel it all ♪
♪ Around yourself. ♪
_
- _
- (THUNDER CRASHES)
_
Oh. I forgot to unlock the door.
God, how insulting to people.
So nervous about seeing your mother.
Let's just enjoy Portland.
I mean, I can't believe we've
never been here before.
Indigenous artworks, craft breweries,
independent movie theaters...
and that's just in one coffee shop.
(GASPS) Comic Book Guy?
Yes, I often come here to recharge.
In Portland I'm quirky,
rather than objectionable.
Do you sell comic books here?
No. Marijuana. And artisanal salami.
Laced with marijuana.
(ACOUSTIC SIMPSONS THEME PLAYING)
Stupid Flanders Street.
Okay, this is where your mom is.
Help me get her back.
Please help me get her back.
Ooh. Hello, Nicolas Cage.
(GROWLS)
Dad, she's gonna know
that's not your real hair.
You've got to have a modicum
of faith in who you are.
It's a snap.
Cool.
- (KNOCKING ON DOOR)
- Welcome, new friend,
whoever you are.
Homie!
You're here a day early.
BOTH: Mom!
Mm. Oh, I've missed you all so much.
How are you guys?
Oh! We were, of course, unraveling.
Bart, Lisa, your grampa is
taking good care of you.
- (MEOWS)
- Now where's the baby?
Aw. Good girl.
Um, I like what you're wearing.
Thank you. These are
locally-sourced dungarees
and Pendleton flannel.
It's what Jill Sobule wore
when she played the Crystal Ballroom.
(GASPS) Jill Sobule?
Like every other place
we go, I love Portland.
So much, I want to leave Springfield
until I find out something
bad that makes me realize
that there's no place like home.
Now, now, your mother
has not settled in here.
PAULA: Welcome.
These are our pugs: Nike and Swoosh.
BOTH: Mwah.
_
Marjorie, could you and I
have a word in the backyard?
Don't you see what's happening here?
- You're married.
- Yes, I know.
- To you.
- No, to her. Look around.
You're married in the two most
important ways there are:
emotionally and cooking.
(CHUCKLES): Oh. That's ridiculous.
(QUIETLY): You're fostering pugs.
- They remind me of you.
- Aw.
But I am upset. I'm
finally good at something
and you have to be jealous.
Marge, sweetie, I'm really proud of you.
I'm not jealous or mad.
It's just... when are you coming home?
Tomorrow, after the competition.
Woo-hoo! I win.
- Not that I was nervous.
- (PHONE VIBRATING)
_
Unless we win, in which case,
I might stay and prep for the finals.
Marge, I've backed you
in this from day one.
No, you haven't. Not a bit.
Then it's too late to start now.
Oh, I'm sitting in a bar
and my wife's in love
with a female lumberjack.
Classic Portland. Where are you from?
Springfield.
- Which one? Oregon?
- I don't know.
ANNOUNCER: Welcome back
to the Grizzly Timbersports
Northwest Championship Finals,
brought to you by no one.
Still looking.
Marge and Paula are in control.
I am falling in love with this sport.
And when I fall, I fall hard.
I'm taking you home with me.
(CHITTERS)
Hold the Stella, fella.
Carol "Oak" Connor and
Rachel "The Pine" Cohen
have taken command.
♪ ♪
I can't be silent anymore.
Let me through.
- Eh.
- There's plenty of room.
- Marge, I was a lumber-jerk.
- (GRUNTING)
I'm only happy if you're happy.
Our love is like an old tree.
If you cut it down,
it grows back stronger.
(QUIETLY): Um, that's
not how trees work.
Well, according to my book, it is.
_
(GRUNTING)
- Yay! All right.
- (CHEERING)
I love this sport!
And maybe now I can
love my lumberjack son.
(CRYING)
Ladies and gentlemen, our grand champion
and winner of a Bass Pro
Shops $50 gift card,
Marge Simpson.
- (EXCLAIMS)
- All right, champ!
See you in the showers.
Congratulations, Paula.
You won. Enjoy the hell out of her.
Homer, what is it you
think that I've won?
With me, Marge is a good woman.
With you, Marge is a great woman
with two awesome dogs.
I'm not interested in Marge.
- I have a wife and a kid.
- You have a wife?
She's in Tokyo,
training for the Olympics.
She dances... with the ribbons?
I don't know what it's called.
So you're not breaking us up?
No. I mean, I'll miss her on
the other end of the bucksaw,
and I'll really miss that
$80 grand prize money,
but she's welcome to come
up here and train any time.
I am so grateful. I want
to do something for you.
If you'd like another kid,
I am more than happy
to offer up my sperm.
That's very kind, but...
No really, I've always
wanted to have a kid
with no responsibilities.
All right. You're in the top three.
It's you, the track star
or the Harvard professor.
Oh, I get it.
Instead of sperm, would you like semen?
- They're the same thing.
- They are? Uh-oh.
Oh, it still feels weird.
I don't know what to say to her.
(WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY)
I never would've thought of that.
Honey, would you like to come home?
Aw. Okay.
Your daddy loves you, sweetie.
He wants to make sure
you're always a strong,
confident little lady.
So I went out and got you this.
Mwah.
(BUZZES)
Aw, her baby head fell out.
You'll be getting a visit
from the Head Fairy.
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
♪ I walked out of the forest ♪
♪ Before we said goodbye ♪
♪ The birds were all a-singing ♪
♪ As she pointed to the sky ♪
♪ She said, "Can't
you see the rainbow? ♪
♪ They made it just for you" ♪
♪ She handed me her toolbox ♪
♪ Said, "Now you know what to do" ♪
♪ Vroom, vroom, pull the cord ♪
♪ Buzz, buzz, just one more ♪
♪ Roar, roar, what a thrill ♪
♪ With Lumberjill ♪
♪ Vroom, vroom, pull the cord ♪
♪ Buzz, buzz, just one more ♪
♪ Roar, roar, what a thrill ♪
♪ With Lumberjill. ♪