Previously on
"Better Call Saul"...
You done?
Not yet.
Mike: In a few days,
Howard Hamlin's car
will be found several states
away.
There will be cocaine in
the upholstery.
That's the story you were
setting up for this guy, yeah?
So, you two are gonna
go about your day,
normal, same as ever.
You keep telling the lie
that you've been telling.
It's the per-r-r-r-fe-e-e-e-ct
Wa-a-a-a-a-a-a-y
To end a per-r-r-r-fe-e-e-e-ct
Da-a-a-a-a-y
It's the per-r-r-r-fe-e-e-e-ct
Wa-a-a-a-a-a-a-y
To end a per-r-r-r-fe-e-e-e-ct
Da-a-a-a-a-y
Ride with me
Glide with me
Stay by my side with me
Through the night
Ride on the wings
Of the angels of love
Who are on our side
Ahh, ahh, ahh, ahh, ahh
It's the per-r-r-r-fe-e-e-e-ct
Wa-a-a-a-a-a-a-y
To end a per-r-r-r-fe-e-e-e-ct
Da-a-a-a-a-y
Ahh, ahh, ahh, ahh, ahh, ahh
Ahh, ahh, ahh
It's the per-r-r-r-fe-e-e-e-ct
Wa-a-a-a-a-a-a-y
To end a per-r-r-r-fe-e-e-e-ct
Da-a-a-a-a-y
Ride with me
Glide with me
Stay by my side
through the night
Ride on the wings
Of the angels of love
Who are on our side
Ahh, ahh, ahh, ahh, ahh
To say
I
Love
You
One day, we'll, uh...
we'll wake up
and brush our teeth
and we'll go to work...
and at some point
we'll suddenly realize...
that we haven't thought
about it at all.
None of it.
And that's when we'll know.
We'll know we can forget.
Gus: Don Eladio.
Don Juan.
Gustavo.
Don Hector.
Gustavo...
"Ding! Ding! Ding!
Ding! Ding! Ding!
Ding! Ding! Ding! Ding! Ding!
Ding! Ding! Ding! Ding!"
"Ding! Ding! Ding! Ding!"
Ay, ay, ay.
Ahh.
Bueno.
Gustavo...
The doc left these for you,
in the event
that you made it back alive.
Tell me about the lawyers.
Well, they spent a full
afternoon with the cops.
Played it as they were told.
Maybe a bit better.
The APD consensus is
he walked into the ocean
and killed himself.
Without a body,
they can't close the file,
but for all practical purposes
it's over.
When can construction resume?
We need to find a new engineer
and a crew to do the work.
That could take some time.
Start today.
Bartender:
Mr. Fring. Welcome back.
Well, thank you, Brett.
What can I get you?
Wine, to start.
Yes, sir.
A glass of the
Dressler & Vaughn, please.
Right away.
Mr. Fring.
It's so good to see you.
It's been a while.
Yes. Too long.
What are you drinking?
The Dressler & Vaughn.
How is it?
Enough said.
Brett?
Can you get that bottle
from before?
Now, normally,
we would never have this open,
but a couple hours ago,
I smelled cigar smoke.
And I look up
and this Cadillac cowboy
is rolling in,
puffing on a Monte Cristo.
And, I mean,
we're talking the full deal.
You know, Stetson
and ostrich skin boots,
the belt buckle
the size of Utah.
On his arm, there's a...
A young woman
who somehow poured herself
into the tightest dress
that I have ever seen...
Anyway, he clearly
wants to impress his date,
so he orders this.
He takes one sip,
and sends it back.
For a rum and Coke.
DietCoke.
What can I say?
But his loss
is definitely your gain.
Remarkable.
Mm-hmm.
I thought you'd like it.
It is from the birthplace
of Syrah, Côte-Rtie.
This one is Rene Rostaing's
La Landonne.
So, I'm in college.
And I make it to Europe,
my first time.
And I got a little enthusiastic
with my Eurail pass.
Long story short, I get lost.
And I mean really lost.
It is the middle of the night,
pitch black.
I'm standing on
this cobblestone street
with my backpack
and there's no one around.
I mean, I have absolutely
no idea where I am.
Finally, I get to
this stand of cedar trees
and I just go ahead and roll out
the sleeping bag.
And the next morning I wake up
and...
I'm in paradise.
Ampuis.
It's... It's...
It's this perfect little village
in the southeast.
It's... It's surrounded by
vineyards, everything's... green.
They call it the ancient gateway
to the Rhône Valley.
They've been making wine there
since Roman times.
Am I talking too much?
No, not at all.
The vineyards are so steep
they can't get tractors
up there, so they use horses.
Still, to this day.
Do you get that, um...
That meaty... it's
almost bloody flavor?
The soil is all iron oxide
and manganese.
You can taste it
in the glass, right?
I have a confession to make.
About a year ago,
you mentioned a rare vintage
from the same region.
1978?
Yes. Exactly.
And I must say, you paint
a compelling picture.
I went home that night,
and I bought a bottle.
A 1978 Côte-Rtie?
Mm-hmm.
Mr. Fring,
that must... Gustavo.
Gustavo.
I'm saving it
for a special occasion.
Well, I would love
to hear about it...
when you have that occasion.
Hold on. There's something
I have to show you.
The owner bought a bottle
of Guigal.
I can't open it. Of course.
But the bottle itself is...
You'll appreciate this.
I'll be right back.
Brett.
Would you let David know
that I've been called away?
Brett:
Of course, Mr. Fring.
Have a good evening. Thank you.
Yes?
Mike: Mr. Varga,
you don't know me,
but I'd like to talk
about your son.
My son?
What happened?
Maybe we could talk
face-to-face...?
I'm outside.
Who are you?
It's not important.
I saw you here before.
Chrysler Fifth Avenue.
What about my son?
I'm sorry.
He won't be found.
It was over fast.
No pain.
You were there?
I wasthere.
Your son made some mistakes.
He fell in with bad people.
But he was never like them,
not really.
He had a good heart.
One more thing.
You won't have to worry
about the Salamancas.
Their day is coming.
There will be justice.
Justice?
I'm sorry.
My Spanish.
J-Justicia.
Justice.
What you talk about
is not justice.
What you talk of is revenge.
It never ends.
My boy is gone.
Oh, they got a new trashcan.
We'll just put in an appearance.
Twenty minutes tops.
We can get through
twenty minutes of anything.
There's Julie and Francis.
Hey, Kim.
Hey, guys.
Jimmy.
I always admired him.
Always.
Even when...
I mean, nobody could relate
to a client quite like he could.
And it wasn't an act.
He genuinely cared.
I never saw it coming...
Addiction is a disease.
He was a good lawyer
and a hell of a guy.
What else is there to say?
It still
doesn't seem real.Mm.
I mean, I...
expect to see him
charging down those stairs
with a big grin on his face.
You know,
this is probably the last time
any of us will be
in this building.
Why is that?
Uh, HMM is downsizing.
Seriously? Yep.
They're gonna take
half a floor downtown.Hmm.
And they're changing their name.
Changing their name to what?
Uh... Brookner Partners?
Something like that.
End of an era.
Yeah.
Have you spoken to Cheryl?
Um, not yet.
To not even have a body
to put in the ground...
I heard she took a leave
from her practice.
Maybe we should go up there
and pay our respects.
Yeah.
Rich, good to see you.
I wish it was under
better circumstances.
You too, Kim.
Take care.
Jimmy... ah, Saul.
Bye, Rich.
Cliff.
Kim. Jimmy. Kim, hi.
Hi, Cheryl.
Um, I'm Jimmy McGill.
You may not remember me.
I'm Chuck McGill's brother.
Of course.
Very sorry for your loss.
Cheryl, I'm so sorry.
I can't even imagine
what you must be going through.
If Jimmy and I can do anything
for you or your family,
please just say the word.
There is something, actually.
You two were the last ones
to see him, weren't you?
Um...
I guess so.
Um, that's what the police said.
Howard told me
that you were harassing him.
Playing elaborate pranks
of some sort.
That you wouldn't
leave him alone.
I know he thought that.
H-He told me, as well.
Um, I think
he honestly believed it.
But you're denying it.
You know what?
I didn't leave here
under the best, uh, terms.
The past few years,
I could have, uh,
been more considerate to Howard
instead of yitzing him
every chance I got.
I guess, uh...
there was a certain amount
of jealousy on my part
because Howard had the, uh,
respect of my brother.
Which I never did.
Tell me what you told
the police.
Okay. Um well,
I mean, it was 11:00 P.M.
Howard started
pounding on our door.
He was very upset,
going on about something,
uh, he thought was my fault.
Uh, I guess it had to do
with the Sandpiper case,
but I-I couldn't make
head or tail out of it.
We tried to calm him down...
But he just... he just wouldn't.
Um...
Finally, he left.
That... That's it.
I'm not oblivious.
I know people are saying
he was on drugs.
Is that what
you're trying to tell me?
It just...
He just didn't
seem like himself.
Are you hearing all of this?
Because none of it
makes sense to me.
Main: Cheryl,
maybe we should just...
I don't care
what people are saying.
what the police think.
Howard was not on drugs.
That simply is not true.
There's something more to this.
I don't know if it's my place,
but...
I... I...
Please... just spit it out.
It was about
a year and a half ago.
I was still an associate here.
Working late on a brief.
And I saw a light on
in Howard's office.
I assumed the cleaning crew
left it on by mistake.
And I was sure the office
was empty, so I didn't knock...
And?
And Howard was there
at his desk,
head down,
and he was snorting something.
I looked at him.
He looked at me.
I didn't know what to do,
so I just walked out.
And the next morning
when we saw each other,
neither of us said
anything about it.
I never told anyone...
but now I wish I had.
In all the years
that you worked with him,
have you witnessed
anything like this?
Even a hint?
Cliff?
I...
Cheryl, this really isn't
the time or the place.
Cheryl, you were his wife.
You... You saw him every day,
you knew him better than anyone.
Maybe I misunderstood
what I saw...
You would have known.
Please excuse me.
Her sister's here somewhere.
I'm... I'm gonna go find her.
I know that was tough,
um, but it's over now.
I mean really over.
Let the healing begin.
Bailiff: All rise.
Court is now in session.
The Honorable Judge Dearden
presiding.
Good afternoon.
We are here to discuss
a motion to exclude evidence
in State of New Mexico
v. Yarborough.
Your Honor, if I may?
I submitted
an additional motion.
I'm assuming
you have not seen it yet.
Did we get that? It just came in,
Judge.
I apologize.
It was a last minute addition.
Last minute is right.
Do I understand this correctly?
You're requesting to withdraw
from this case?
Yes, Your Honor.
My client is fully informed
and I've already been in touch
with another attorney.
Paige Novick.
She's highly qualified
and familiar with the case.
She's prepared to step in,
if you'll allow it.
Ms. Wexler, Mr. Orenstein,
approach the bench.
Ms. Wexler, we are here today
at yourinsistence,
to consider yourmotion,
to exclude evidence.
And this is the moment
you choose to withdraw?
It was unavoidable.
May I ask why?
Personal reasons, Your Honor.
Personal reasons.
Are we talking about
a health issue?
Something to do with
a loved one?
No.
Would you rather discuss this
privately in chambers?
Thank you
for the consideration...
but no.
Would you care to supply
any detail at all?
Your Honor, I'd prefer not to.
Mr. Orenstein,
is the state prepared
to discuss Ms. Wexler's motion?
We are, Your Honor.
Absolutely.
You know what,
Ms. Wexler?
Mr. Orenstein is here.
I'm here.
We all showed up for your party
and now you're taking away
the punchbowl?
I'm inclined to have you
argue your motion
and then I'll consider
late-arriving petitions.
I'm sorry for wasting
the court's time, Your Honor,
but it's impossible for me
to continue with this hearing.
And why is that,
Ms. Wexler?
Because I'm no longer
an attorney.
I'm sorry? What?
I gave notice to the bar
two hours ago.
You did what?!
Why... why?!
All right, all right.
I know why.
But, Kim,
you can't just... Jimmy, I-I...
Shh. Just let me
say my piece, okay?
Just...
Let's take a breath here.
Kim, after everything
that happened...
I mean, Jesus.
I get it.
You want to climb
out of your own skin.
That's natural.
But, Kim, you don't just
throw everything away.
Th-This is your life.
You're a lawyer.
Wh... uh, what about
your clients, huh?
What about, uh, that poor guy,
uh, Mr. Yarborough?
What about the kid
in foster care?
Huh? You give them
everything you've got.
Who are they gonna find
who's half as good as you?
No one!
They need you.
It's already done. Ugh!
Okay.
What's done can be undone.
All I'm saying is
just... just...
Let's take a week or two
to think it over.
For now, we're gonna take
some time off.
God knows we need it.
We're gonna find a new place.
We're gonna leave here.
We're never, ever gonna
come back here again, okay?
We're gonna...
We're gonna put it behind us.
Things will look brighter.
I guarantee it.
But first, we have to fix this.
So we're gonna go back
to the hotel room,
and you're gonna write letters.
You're gonna write a letter
to the bar.
You're gonna write letters
to your clients.
Y-You... You dictate.
I will type.
We're gonna roll
this thing back.
I'll order a pizza.
We'll pull an all-nighter
because we're in this
together, okay?
So, I'm gonna go get
your... your printer
and then we're gonna get
the hell out of here.
Look, Jimmy... J-Jimmy...
You asked
if you were bad for me.
Kim: That's not it.
We are bad for each other.
Kim.
Don't do this.
Kim, please.
Jimmy.
I have had the time
of my life with you.
But we are bad
for everyone around us.
Other people suffer
because of us.
Apart, we're okay,
but together...
we're poison.
No. No.
Just tell me
what I need to do
to change, okay?
Just tell me what it is
and I'll do it.
Jimmy.
No, Kim.
You make me happy.
We make each other happy.
How can that be bad?
Hey.
I love you.
I love you, too.
But so what?
No. No.
No, Kim, you're wrong!
This is about Howard!
Okay? What happened to him
wasn't on us.
It wasn't your fault.
It wasn't my fault!
It was that fucking
Lalo Salamanca!
That psychopath came back
from the dead
and he walked through that door!
He did this.
Not us. Him.
I knew.
You knew wh-what?
I knew he was alive.
No, you didn't.
It was about a month ago.
I saw that car
following me again.
And it turned out
that Mike Ehrmantraut
had guys watching both of us.
Watching for Lalo.
Mike... Mike told you
that Lalo was alive...
and you didn't tell me?
Jimmy, I thought...
I thought it was
a one in a million chance
that he'd come for us.
I thought he would be caught
if he did.
And I told myself
I was protecting you.
But that's not the truth.
The...
The real reason
I didn't tell you
was because
I knew what you'd do.
Wh... What would I do?
You'd... You'd blame yourself.
You'd fear for me.
You'd want us to run and hide
until you were sure I was safe.
You would pull the plug
on the scam.
And then...
And then, uh...
we'd break up.
And I didn't want that.
Because I was having
too much fun.
Any way you want it,
that's the way you need it
Any way you want it
She loves to laugh
She loves to sing
She does everything
She loves to move
She loves to groove
Rise and shine, time to go.
Hit me.
I'm hearing your report didn't
use the magic words, Doc.
Soft. Tissue. Damage.
Doesn't matter
what the X-rays show,
tissue damage
gets my client paid...
Hey, hey.
You're not listening.
My client isn't
just suing your company,
he's coming after you
personally.
Listen, you have a choice, okay?
You can pay up now
or, uh, bleed to death in court.
So, I say be smart
and write that check.
You have till E.O.D.
I'm so sorry.
I'm getting another call.
Got it.
What else you got?
Oh, that's my Xanax guy.
Uh, tell him yes and today...
Another public masturbator?
Which one?
A new guy? Huh.
Everyone must be doing it...
What do you mean,
he hasn't paid?
I saw him give you the card.
A fake?
That sneaky little jackass.
Tell him he'll be spending
St. Patrick's Day in Los Lunas
unless he comes up
with the cash ASAP.
Wait. Shut up. Shut up.
I got a good one.
Did you see a bus went off I-40
up near Gates?
Eighteen people injured.
Uh, don't we know a kid,
an intern at the hospital
up there, had a bunch of DUls?
What was his name?
Breakfast bar,
go ahead, take one.
I'm not...
I'm not talking to you.
Uh, Ramirez. Ramirez.
Yes. Call that kid.
Tell him I want the names
and numbers of all the victims.
I smell class action.
And then get the kid
with the camera.
Send him up there.
And then call the newspaper
and say that Saul Goodman
is outraged
at the
"Fiery Fiasco on the Forty."
That's what we're gonna call it.
Move it to court day.
I'm... I'm not going down there
twice in one week.
That's their problem...
Send a messenger
with, uh, Beanie Babies
and an Edible Arrangement
with extra dipped pineapple.
It's... Shut up. Shut up. Saul
on radio: Better Call Saul!
Auto insurance won't pay
for your fender bender?
Ripped off
by your brother-in-law?
Major or minor surgery
gone wrong?
I'm here for you, Albuquerque.
Better Call Saul!
Call 505-503-4...
Did you hear that?
It's in mono.
I'm not paying
for that muffled crap.
Mono!
It's what The Beatles used.
It's ancient.
Look, I sound like I'm in a well
inside of a cave
under a blanket.
I'm... Who wants a lawyer
who you can't hear?
Here's what you do.
Stop the check ASAP,
then call the station manager.
You tell them if the ad
doesn't make my ears bleed
the next time it plays,
I will see him in court.
Screw the FCC!
I'll go to the mat
with those pencil-pushers.
Ugh.
This is textbook
freedom of speech.
What could be more American
than that?
I'm a Yankee Doodle Dandy.
Get all that? Call the bank.
Cancel the check.
Call the station manager.
Tell him to crank it up
or I'll see him
in court. Got it.
Move.
What?
Alright. Let justice be done
though the heavens fall.
And ready, set, action!
Move, move, move!
Go, go, go!
One, Armani suits and run!
Two, Air Jordan shoes for you!
Three, linen shirts for free!
Four, cashmere sweaters
out the door!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!