Inside. In the kitchen.
Yeah.
Where are you?
I don't know.
I've only been...
...been heading north
for about two hours.
I crossed a river
maybe an hour ago.
Anybody see you?
No.
Keep it that way.
You're in Salamanca territory.
Everybody's gonna be
on the lookout for you.
And I mean everybody.
That includes the Federales.
Is it done?
Yeah. He's dead.
There were some...
regular people...
at that house, some old folks.
What about them?
Got no information on that.
When we hang up,
take the battery
out of your phone.
Head north.
Stay out of sight.
I'm fixing up a place for you
to lie low.
In an hour,
you put the battery back in
and I'll call you
and tell you where to go.
Don Eduardo.
Are you all right?
An accident.
Sorry to trouble you.
May I come in?
Of course!
Gracias.
Sugar, milk?
No need. Thank you.
Delicious!
What's wrong?
Don Eduardo is here!
Don Eduardo...
So good to see you!
I'd shake your hand, but...
Look at you! Mountain man!
You look like ZZ Top!
ZZ--?
Clean up for Don Eduardo!
Go wash, shave!
Oh sure!
I'm sorry, Don Eduardo.
Go!
Excuse me.
Hey, Mateo.
Keep the mustache and
the soul patch. It looks good.
Yes, Don Eduardo.
You're sure
you don't want breakfast?
The eggs are fresh from
this morning.
How are Mateo's teeth doing?
Better?
Yes! Your dentist
worked so hard!
Matti used to be up all night
with the pain.
Now he sleeps like a baby.
Thanks to you, Don Eduardo.
That's good, Sylvia.
And the goats?
From your hometown?
They don't miss the mountains?
They're fine.
We're expecting
two more next month.
You sent for more?
Cabritos. Babies.
Mm.
You're almost finished.
I'll make more.
You're sure about breakfast?
Just coffee is fine.
It's all right?
Very handsome.
Hey.
So, uh, what's on
the agenda?
Uh, well, I just got
20 new clients from Grant, so--
Twenty?
Yeah.
I have meetings with four
of them this afternoon,
and a preliminary hearing
with Flaherty first thing.
Juvenile.
What about you?
Mm.
Same thing.
Huge day.
Yes, your mother
and your grandmother.
If they can take time off
from work, both of them.
Do you have any uncles or--?
Oh, yeah. That would be great.
Do you have anything nice
to wear?
Like a sports coat, or...
a collared shirt?
Hey.
You know what?
I'll bring something for you.
That's too nice.
No, it's no problem.
You know how
to get there?
Tijeras and Fifth.
That's right. Yes.
All right, I will meet you
at 9:30 sharp.
It's gonna be fine, Ronnie.
Well, tell them
it's gonna be fine.
Because it will be.
Okay.
Thanks.
I'll bring it back clean.
Shoot. Do you have any cash
for the taxi?
Crap, all's I got
is 5 bucks.
Um...
Think the cabbie
will break a hundred?
Good morning, Don Juan.
Lalo Salamanca is dead.
Gunmen broke into his hacienda
last night.
Hired operators
from the look of it.
It was messy. Very messy.
As for the Salamancas...
"Sangre por sangre."
Yes. That is the Salamanca way.
We are on the verge of chaos.
But who did this?
One minute,
I hear talk of the Colombians.
The next, traitors.
Traitors close to home.
We know this much.
Ignacio Varga is a rat.
Don Eladio has put a price
on his head.
Every man we have
is searching for him.
When Varga's found,
we'll know who he was
working for.
I assume Don Hector
has been told.
I called him myself.
As for if he understood me,
quién sabe.
Listen to me.
You must be careful, Gustavo.
This is a dangerous time.
No one is above suspicion.
I understand.
Good.
Tell me again about the sicario
who made the final report.
He was already wounded
when he talked to our cut-out.
Federales found him dead
at the scene.
But they got Salamanca.
The mercenaries are dead
to a man.
And yet, their mission
was a success.
It has been known
to happen.
I could go down there
and get Varga,
bring him home safe.
There's ways to do it
on the quiet.
Unless you already
have something in the works.
Speak your mind.
Loyalty goes both ways.
Varga's done everything
you asked him.
He wasn't given
a choice.
Maybe so, but he played
a tough game.
And he played it
on the square.
And?
When all is said and done,
the kid deserves your respect.
He has it.
Is there more
you wish to say?
I hope this brings your guy
more luck than it brought me.
You good?
I'm great.
Detective. Miss Khalil.
Good morning.
I've been calling you
for two days.
Well, my girl's out sick.
What can I do you for?
Tomorrow morning,
10 a.m.
Brunch? But just you and me,
right?
I mean, won't the big fella here
feel like a third wheel?
You and I are meeting
Parson in chambers.
I am asking for
an emergency hearing
to alter the terms
of De Guzman's release.
That sounds like a blast.
Unfortunately,
I'm booked solid.
I checked your client's
place of residence.
The address he gave?
It's a Dairy Queen
in Alta Monte.
The family that showed
at the bail hearing
can't be located.
No driver's license,
no tax rolls,
no school records, nothing.
Fact is, there isn't a single
Elizabeth McKinnon
under the age of 73
living in New Mexico.
Well, this is--
This is surprising.
Your client
has disappeared,
and I'm not waiting six weeks
to start looking for him.
Hey, my guy put up
7 million in bail.
You think he's just
gonna walk away from that?
Who comes up with 7 million
bucks in cash?
You know
what I think?
I think
the family was fake,
and I think you knew it
the whole time.
Hold up, let's just
get real for a second here.
The hearing didn't go
your way,
and now you're trying
for a do-over.
You say my guy ran?
I say, he's got 7 million
reasons for showing up
when he's legally required
to do so.
So, no, I won't be due process
window dressing
at any crash meeting
with Parson.
And if you try throwing
any of this crap around
in front of the judge
without my presence,
here's an accusation:
prosecutorial misconduct.
Career-ending
None of that changes the fact...
...the guy's not who he said.
No, no, no. Hold on.
You guys got caught with
your pants around your ankles,
and somehow that's on me?
I don't think so.
You've got two dozen lawyers
up there.
You got investigators,
you got the whole damn
police force,
and it's my fault
you can't keep track of Lalo?
That is not my job!
Lalo? Who's Lalo?
What? What did I say?
I meant, De Guzman.
I have more than one client.
So, ahem...
I will see you
at the preliminary in six weeks
as scheduled.
Until then, I have
clients who need me.
Nice threads.
Uh, thanks.
Hey.
Hi.
How'd it go?
The suit
definitely helped.
This kid,
he's a high school senior.
Good grades,
works two jobs,
has this so-called...
friend,
some snot-nosed brat
who drives a brand-new
Mustang convertible.
One Saturday night,
Richie Rich says,
"Hey, you wanna drive
my car?"
How can my guy resist?
The friend tells him
to pull over at a liquor store.
Rich kid goes in,
robs the place with
his uncle's bowie knife.
No.
Yeah.
My guy's out in the Mustang,
playing with the radio.
He's got no idea.
Rich kid comes out
with 425 in cash,
bottle of Jägermeister,
tells my guy to floor it,
which he does, happily,
because he's completely
in the dark about the robbery.
Yeah, but when they pick him up,
your kid is driving.
He's driving, yes.
Of course he's driving.
My guy ends up
with a public defender.
Rich kid's family brings in
a top-dollar defense
from out of state,
if you can believe it, Denver,
and they're trying to dump
the whole thing on my guy.
It was my client's idea,
he was forcing the rich kid
into it, the whole deal.
Oakley's going for aggravated
robbery and assault.
Oakley? That dick. Yeah.
But your kid was never even
inside the store.
Flaherty forced joinder,
but I--
I think I can
make it work for us.
Trial's next month.
This was really good.
Have some.
You want anything?
Uh...
You should definitely
try these.
Excuse me?
Sure.
Can we get a menu and another
order of sopaipillas?
You got it.
Thank you.
And there was
a homeless woman
that I had to get
out of MDC.
That's another story.
Sounds like the day from hell.
It was one of the best days
of my life.
My professional life.
How about you?
I rented us a car.
It's-- It's the Ford.
So Saul Goodman drives
a brown Ford Taurus?
Detroit calls that taupe,
I believe.
Don't you think Saul Goodman
would drive something
with a little more...flair?
Such as?
I don't know.
Definitely American-made.
Something showy.
And Saul Goodman
has an office.
Something eye-catching.
Good location.
By the courthouse?
Yeah.
A cathedral of justice.
Oh! A cathedral of justice.
Okay. Yeah.
We should start looking
for something for you.
I mean for "Saul."
Sold. When do we start?
Saturday's good.
Saturday it is.
I was thinking
about our first move.
On the Howard front.
I think there's a way
to get Sandpiper settled
and leave him standing.
Bruised, maybe,
but still standing.
Maybe the trick is,
we're not working on Howard,
not at first.
Maybe we start
with Cliff Main.
So, uh...
we're doing that?
I thought we were.
Aren't we?
You think we shouldn't.
Well, I-- I didn't say that. Um...
Here we are.
Did you decide on anything?
No, not yet.
Can I get you a drink
while you're thinking about it?
Uh, yeah. A Coke. Thanks.
All right.
Here you go.
Okay.
So the, uh...
...the Howard thing.
Wh-- What were you thinking?
You sure?
What's the harm
in listening?
Well, heh...
it has to be paced right.
We move too fast,
they'll see us coming.
And it has to make sense.
It doesn't have to stand up
in court,
but there has to be a reason
for everything.
Yeah.
I'm at the motel.
No one saw me
but the lady who runs it.
All right. We're working
on getting you out.
It's gonna take
a couple of days.
I'll call you when our guys
are set up.
They're gonna be driving
a farm truck.
When they pass,
you jump in the back.
It's gonna happen fast.
They're not gonna wait for you.
There's some clothes
in the closet.
Wear them.
What happens
between now and then?
Stay out of sight.
Eladio put a price
on your head.
Anyone comes through
that door, you shoot.
You got it?
Yeah.
Here you go.
Thanks.
No, you see,
you build it too high,
your marble's gonna run
off the track.
It's not finished.
When it's finished,
it'll work.
Okay.
May I please have
some more lemonade?
No. You drank
about a gallon already.
Please, Pop-pop.
All right,
one more and that's it.
Thank you, Pop-pop.
Three...
Four...
Five...
Six...
Oh, wait.
There they are.
Oh, yeah.
Okay,
they're on the fourth hole.
Assuming they're playing nine,
that should give you about...
45 minutes, safely.
You gotta teach me
to play golf.
A lawyer should be able
Any time.
You all right?
Yup.
Piece of cake.
Excuse me, sir.
Are you a member
or a guest?
I'm just here for a tour.
Oh, welcome.
Front desk
is straight ahead.
Hi, I called about a tour?
Oh, if you'll follow me
to the members' lounge?
Hi. Norm Wakely.
I understand you're
in the market for a tour?
That's right.
Saul Goodman.
Great to meet you,
Mr. Goodman.
Oh, please, call me Saul. Great.
So, Saul, can I get you
anything before we get started?
The coffee here
is just unbeatable.
Uh, well, I'm fine.
I'm fully caffeinated.
Well, Saul, you and I
are standing on hallowed ground.
Five presidents have played
on our course...
Oh, really?
...starting with Eisenhower.
But the story goes back
even further than that--
Norm! Can I have a sec, please?
Kevin, hey,
how's it going?
Uh, I'm sorry.
I'm sure this will just
be a moment.
Mr. Goodman...
I'm so sorry,
but I've just been reminded
that, in fact,
we have a two-year
waiting list.
Two years. Wow.
Maybe I could, uh,
go on the tour anyway,
I mean, because I'm here.
Just in case.
Well, unfortunately,
we suspended tours.
For the moment.
You're not even
giving tours?
I apologize
for the inconvenience.
We'll be happy to call you
if the situation changes.
You left your number?
Uh-huh.
Well, we'll be in touch...
if the situation changes.
Again, I-- I'm sorry
for your time and trouble.
Uh, we just--
We had a few crossed wires.
Well...
Okay, then.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Oh, yes?
Just so I understand,
you were gonna give me a tour,
and then you realized
you don't need new members?
We have a waiting list.
Okay, but you're
the membership director,
so you would have
known that before.
I know.
It doesn't really add up.
I mean, I came in and everyone
was rolling out the red carpet,
and then, all of a sudden,
something changed.
I don't...
Mr. Goodman, I--
Goodman.
The name.
The second you heard it,
everything turned
on a dime!
Wow.
Waiting list.
I think you're talking
about an exclusion list.
It's okay. I should've known,
because, I mean, look,
it's wall-to-wall mayonnaise
in here!
So, you know, listen,
if you're gonna be restricted,
have the courage
to say so.
There's no question of--
Here it is, folks!
Anti-Semitism alive and well,
right here in Albuquerque.
Sir, we have many
Jewish members.
Oh, good, well,
you've met your quota, then.
Gold star for you.
Hold on!
That's gotta be the biggest
load of horse crap
I've ever heard in my life.
Go crawl back in your hole,
McGill, or Goodman,
whatever you're calling yourself.
What are you up to,
anyway?
Ginning up another one
of your put-up job lawsuits,
you two-faced,
blackmailing,
money-grubbing
son of a bitch--
"Money-grubbing"? You're saying
the quiet part out loud.
Gentlemen, can we just keep
the volume down?
You know that's not
what I meant.
In this day and age,
I'd hoped and prayed
we'd be beyond this.
You're about as Jewish
as my Aunt Fannie--
Five thousand years
and it never ends.
Here it is. Violence!
It always comes to this!
Mr. Wachtell, please.
Come on, Kev.
You go to hell,
you lying sack of shit.
Sir...
Mr. Goodman,
I don't know what to say.
That is not--
I wouldn't be a member here.
I wouldn't walk through
those doors again
after what happened to me
here today.
Do you...
at least have a bathroom
that I could use?
Seeing as how my...
Stress like that is hell
on my diverticulitis.
The men's locker room
is the closest.
It's straight through there.
And I would be allowed
to go in there?
Yes. Of course.
I want you to know
I don't blame you personally.
I know you were just
following orders.
It's okay, folks!
I'm leaving.
All is well.
Good morning, sir. Morning.
Shit, shit, shit, shit!
I swear it's nothing I did,
but one of your toilets is--
I'll take care of it, sir.
Okay. It's the middle one.
You can't miss it.
Yeah. No--
No problem, sir.
Two-two-seven.
Went better than last time.
Well, keep your head down,
you'll get better.
Anyway, on the topic
of your hiring binge--
Hardly a "binge."
What would you
call it?
I'd call it
"prudent expansion."
We're not headhunting
any of your associates,
if that's what
you're worried about.
Need a towel?
Sure.
Hey.
Listen, on the QT,
I'd be particularly careful
with any lateral hires.
You're talking
about what's-his-name,
the guy from Tennessee?
You hear something?
Nothing I'd care
to repeat.
Just "trust, but verify."
Fair enough.
Howard.
What?
This can't be.
Sure looks like it.
Really?
Not the first time I've seen
one of those, unfortunately.
Where did it come from?
Didn't it just fall out
of your locker?
I don't see how.
You don't think one of
the members could have--?
Maybe somebody on staff.
Oh.
Where were you?
I'll tell you later.
Here they come.
Did they find it?
Yes.
What if they figure out
it's baby powder?
They won't.
I think maybe
we outsmarted ourselves.
Maybe this was all
too subtle.
Nope. Not too subtle.
Perfect.
Andale. Chop chop.
We don't got all day, folks.
When do we leave?
We go when we go.
I'm gonna need a minute.
Nobody's waiting for you,
big stuff.
What? Be nice.
Hello, Casa Tranquila.
I'm sorry.
Let me get someone
who speaks Spanish.
Oh, no, no. No problem.
I would just like to speak
to one of your residents,
if I may.
Hector, are you awake?
You have another
telephone call.
LALO,
Uncle? Can you hear me?
Do you know my voice?
They told you about the attack,
didn't they?
Let them keep believing
I'm dead.
So much the better.
It was the chicken man.
That coward sat up there
in the north
while his paramilitaries
came into my home--
My home, Uncle!
Screw Bolsa, screw Eladio.
I'm coming north.
I'm going to hurt him.
Hurt him like you taught me.
And then I will kill him.
What is it?
Hector?
Excuse me. I'm so sorry,
but Hector seems a little upset.
Yeah, sorry, um... I'm just--
I'm sharing a bit
of family news.
Some good, some bad.
Would you mind
putting him back on?
It'll only be a minute.
Of course.
Uncle?
What is it?
Do you have another idea?
Okay. Let's see.
A, B, C, D,
E, F, G, H,
I, J, K, L,
M, N, Ñ, O, P--
P? That's right?
Okay.
What's next?
A, B, C...
L, M, N...
U?
Prueba?
Is that what you're saying?
Proof?
Uncle, I don't have any proof.
For months, I was in the north
watching him,
following his men.
There was nothing.
Wait...
There is proof.
I know where to find it.
Goodbye, Uncle.
You will see me soon.
I changed my mind.
I'm not going.
And?
And you give me back
my money.
There's no refunds, asshole.
I told you...
be nice.
Amigos...
I'm very sorry,
but you're going to
have to find
another way to the north.
Abuela...
Make sure everyone
gets their money back.
Be careful.