Previously
on "Better Call Saul"...
Four for unlock,
five for lock.
I gotta tell ya,
it does not sound like
the Howard Hamlin
that I know.
You're going to forget you ever
heard the name Howard Hamlin.
Lalo is dead.[Exhales sharply]
The DA's office
put it together
that Lalo was calling himself
"de Guzman."
What do you think
we should do?
Do you want to be a friend
of the cartel
or do you want to be
a rat?
-What did you learn?
-Lalo Salamanca lives.
[Bicycle gears whirring,
chain clicks]
[The Dreamliners' "The Best
Things in Life"plays]
♪
[Bell rings]
♪ Do-doo-do-do
♪ Do-doo-do,
do-doo-doo-do-do ♪
♪ Do-doo-do-do
♪ Do-doo-do
♪ A shady tree
♪ You and me
♪ So young and free
♪ Yes, these are
the best things in life ♪
♪ Right place
[Bell rings]♪ A warm embrace
♪ A smiling face
♪ Yes, these are
the best things in life ♪
♪ Do-doo-do-do
♪ Do-doo-do,
do-doo-doo-do-do ♪
♪ Do-doo-do-do
♪ Do-doo-do,
do-doo-doo-do-do ♪
Oh, no.
Really?
I thought it'd be
just the trim.
Of all the colors,
why would you pick that?
Use adobe red,
if you want red.
What do you even
call that?
Fire engine red?
Tomato red.
Their poor
neighbors.
Mmh.
♪
♪ Do-doo-do-do
♪ Do-doo-do,
do-doo-doo-do-do ♪
♪ Do-doo-do-do, do-doo-do
♪ So come and fly
♪ Right through the sky
♪ And tell your guy
Ugh.
What an eyesore.
There's no way
the Homeowners' Association
approved that color.
Barb's gonna have a cow.
Whew.
Maybe I could put a bug
in her ear...
What can Barb do?
That place isn't even
in Mountain View.
It's Enchantment Hills
over there.
Enchantment Hills starts
at Pinon Lane.
Remember when the Westlakes
planted those Quaking Aspens?
That whole mess?
I thought
the Westlakes proved
their lot was in
Enchantment Hills.
They paid for
a land survey.
Really?
Where'd you hear that?
Robbie Davis, maybe.
I'll double-check the map
after I shower.
♪
Want some?
Nah. I'm good.
♪
♪ Do-doo-do-do
♪ Do-doo-do,
do-doo-doo-do-do ♪
Is that iced tea?
♪ Do-doo-do,
do-doo-doo-do-do ♪Mrs. Ryman:
Would you like some?
Love some.
Thank you, Ma'am.
♪ So come and fly
♪ Right through the sky
♪ And tell your guy
♪ That these are
the best things in life ♪
♪ Do-doo-do-do, do-doo-do
♪
[Benny Green's "Glidin' Along"
playing]
♪
[Gearshift clicks,
engine shuts off, music stops]
[Birds chirping]
[Car alarm beeps]
[Groans]
[Sighs]
How's it going?
Eh. Status quo.
You know,
hummin' along.
We did land a pretty big client
last week, though.
Insurance outfit
in Santa Fe.
They cover most of the high-end
real estate up there.
Great.
But, Howard,
I'm not a shareholder.[Both chuckle]
I'm... I'm just
getting warmed up.
Although I still think you would
make one hell of litigator.
Ah. Appreciate that,
but I'll pass.
At home, things are
more or less the same.
It's not any worse...
I guess I should be grateful
for that.
It's like we're...
deadlocked.
Cheryl still won't talk about
anything...important.
You tried
what we discussed?
Yes.
Yes, Idid, but...
I didhave a dream.
♪
So I look over
the old man's ticket,
and it's clearly
an international flight,
so we search for
his gate number...
but all the signs are
in a language I can't read.
♪
[Car alarm beeps]
[Sighs]
[Engine starts]
[Benny Green's "Glidin' Along"
plays]
[Music shuts off]
[Exhales sharply]
♪
[Sighs]
[Chair thudding]
[Birds chirping]
♪
[Metal scraping]
[Indistinct conversations]
♪
Kim!
Any traffic?
Nope. Straight shot
down 25.
This is us.
Thanks for meeting me.
I imagine you're swamped
when you're in town.
Today's not too bad.
In fact, I have a meeting
at your old stomping ground,
with Schweikart.
Oh.
Tell Rich I said hi.
Of course.
How's Jimmy?
He's great.
Thanks for asking.
How about Alice?She's doing well.
She's taking up baking,
and, uh, no complaints here.
[Chuckles]
Well, lucky you.Don't I know it.
I hear this place
makes a killer latte.
Yeah.
They give Java Joe's a run
for their money, if you ask me.
[Indistinct shouting]
[Tires screech]
♪
[Horn honking]
[Woman coughing]
♪
[Woman coughs]
Jimmy: Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Come on!
Had a customer.
Okay, okay,
but it's time to go.
C'mon!
We gotta get moving!
♪
Wait.
What are ya doing?
No, no, no, no, no.
Hey. Come on.
We gotta move.
I'm getting a root beer.
No, no.
We have a schedule.
Remember?
We discussed it.
I put two quarters in.
I will buy you an entire case
when we're done.
Here we go.
Right in. Whew.
All the way.
♪
[Tires screech]
[Tires screech,
gearshift clicks]
[Sighs]
[Keypad beeps]
[Exhaling heavily]
[Clears throat]
Everything okay?
Sure.
Do we need to
go over it again?
Nah.
Well, just remember...
keep your feet
out of the way
'cause I'm gonna have to leave
in a hurry.
[Sighs]
What?
I really like
your hair.
It's not... Thank you.
Thanks.
[Sighs]
What if there was
a different way?
What if there was an
independent team of lawyers...
maybe four or five
of them...
who were dedicated to taking on
the difficult cases?
I'm not saying a few lawyers
can solve
a massive,
systemic problem,
but they could
make it better.
And why come to me
with this?
♪
Well, if I wanted
to shine you on,
I'd tell you it's because
you're known for
your social conscience.
But the truth is
it's because of your connections
in state government.
You can make things happen.
Fair enough.
Kim, the firm has
a service committee.
I should tell you
to go to them
and get in line with
all the other worthy causes.
But you're putting your money
where your mouth is.
♪
I'm sure you've heard something
about my son's drug problem.
♪
Gregory's struggle
gave me a more, let's say,
personal view
of the legal system.
♪
Kim, I think
you've got something here.
♪
[Slurps]
[Cellphone beeps]
[Gearshift clicks, tires squeal]
You can't skimp
on the support staff.
They're the beating heart
of the operation.
[Tires screeching]I know that's true
in our office...
[Brakes squeal]
No, no! No! No!
Jesus.
You son of a bitch!
[Groans]
[Tires screech]
You twisted deadbeat
piece of shit!
Wasn't that...Howard?
God damn it![Tires screech]
You owe me!
Man:
Ma'am, are you okay?
You owe me!
Ma'am...
I mean...Nobody does that to me!
I don't know.
It happened so fast.
Damn it! He owes me!
What a rip-off!
Damn you!
[Benny Green's "Glidin' Along"
playing]
♪
No. No!
They moved the cone?!
What kinda asshole
moves a cone?!
[Exhales heavily]
Ohh. Crap.
♪
[Gearshift clicks]
[Brakes squeal,
gearshift clicks]
[Tires screech]
[Engine shuts off]
[Exhaling sharply]
[Car beeps]
[Birds chirping]
[Grunting]
[Grunting continues]
Nngh!
[Breathing heavily]
[Car alarm beeps]
[Engine starts]
[Benny Green's "Glidin' Along"
plays]
♪
Hey, listen.
Um...
Be careful, okay?
Okay.
[Sighs]
What?
Five-O.
That kills business
for the rest of the day.
Always hassling me.
Undercover cops?
Yep.
Well, listen, if you ever have
any legal problems,
give me a call,
anytime.
No charge.
Thanks.
[Breathes deeply]
[Suspenseful music plays]
♪
Kim: [Laughing]Jimmy: So I pulled the Jag
into the loading zone
and I start scrapping
with this hunk of metal.
Oh, my God.It was in deep.
Like down-a-well deep.
[Laughing]So I just...wrestled it!
Nngh!
Like a freakin' bear!
And I... nngh!... jam it in
the dirt in front of the Jag.
[Claps hands]
Boom!
Barely made it out of there
by the skin of my teeth.
Who moves cones?!
Who does that?Narcissists.
[Chuckles]
You're damn right.
[Laughs]
So you think
Cliff really bought it, huh?
One hundred percent.
You should have seen his face.
It landed, trust me.
[Sighs]
God, it was beautiful.
[Chuckles]
Oh.
And that is not all.
Spill.
So,
I'm doing the stall,
I'm telling Cliff
what I'm doing,
what I wanna be doing.
All I'm thinking about is
I gotta stretch this out
until you get there.
But then, I don't know,
I kind of got caught up in it.
And then...
Cliff went for it.
I mean, like,
really went for it.
What does that mean?
Like money?
I-I don't think
he'll write a check himself.
But he knows people.
And I think
he'll deliver.
You're kidding.
[Laughing] I know!
How great is that?
This is unbelievable.
Are we on a roll
or are we on a roll?
[Chuckles][Laughing] Geez.
[Sighs]
[Insects chirping]
You ever feel like
you're being followed?
When I dropped Wendy off
at the motel,
she thought she was being
watched by some undercover cops.
But then,
when I drove away,
that same car
was behind me.
Right after I spotted them,
they disappeared.
Well,
you know what they say.
"The wicked flee
when no man pursueth."
You think we're wicked?
No. What?
[Chuckles]
It's just a turn of phrase.
[Boston accent]
I think you're wicked hawt.
[Normal voice] Alright.
Listen to the voice
of experience, okay?
You know why
you're feeling like this?
Because we got away
with it.
It seems too good
to be true.
But trust me,
nobody is following you.
No one knows what we're doing
except for us.
Okay?
Okay.
I get it.
Under the circumstances,
I wouldn't want to be anywhere
near a police station
if I were you either.
[Exhales sharply]
I'll tell you what.
Um, the mahogany
in my conference room
is currently
getting buffed out,
so I'm using my satellite office
at Juan Tabo and Skyline.
I'm letting a nail salon,
you know, use the lobby,
so my office is in the back.
Meet me there at 3:00.
[Briefcase thuds]Great! Thanks.
How's it hanging, Steve-O?[Wand squeals]
Shoes. Belt. Jacket.
I'm sorry. What?
Seriously?
Since when?
It's procedure, sir.
"Sir"? [Chuckles]
[Sighs]
[Keys thud]Why'd Ihit the jackpot?
Never can tell.
[Object thuds]
Hey. How you doing
on this beautiful day?
Did you, uh, catch
that cookie bouquet
that I sent
for Carlos' birthday?
'Cause I put a few extra
white chocolate macadamias
in there, just for you.
What do you need?
Me? Uh - Nothing.
Nothing!
But I have a "friend"
who could use a...
a preliminary hearing
rescheduled.
Uh,
Gonzalez v. New Mexico.
My "friend" is looking for
a Friday around nine a.m...
you know, before the judge's
fourth cup of coffee
because, uh,
caffeine jitters...
they're brutal
on the defense, so...
What "friend"?
[Sighs] I don't believe
you two have met.
[Briefcase opens]
[Indistinct conversations
in distance]
What is this?
A hearing change
request form.
Hey, come on.
It's me...
Look, Mommy.
I just graduated.
I... I can't use a pen.
I have
no opposable thumbs.
[Sign thuds]
[Elevator bell dings]
[Indistinct conversations]
Hey! Hannah Banana!
Hey, yourself.
[Cart rattling]
[Quarters clinking]
[Buttons clicking]
[Whirring]
[Thud]
Come on, Bill.
That's no way to treat a lady.
You got to make love to it,
Bill.
You know, be gentle...
that's the way to do it.
Think Barry White,
think seduction.
[Clunk, thud]
[Flap clangs][Sighs]
Voilà.
[Door bangs]What the hell
is going on?
How come
everyone's treating me
like I'm covered
in oozing pus sores?
I liked you better
when you were just
a regular bottom feeder.
But this...
"This"?
What is "this"?
I understand
advocating for your client.
Deep in my heart,
I get it.
But you scammed the court,
you scammed the judge.
And for what?
To get a murdering
cartel psychopath
back out
on the street?
It's just...
wrong.
That's a lotta big talk, Bill.
Prove it.
Prove it, Bill!
There's proving,
and then there's knowing.
[Door closes]
Abe, you don't want to go back
to county, do you?
Nuh-uh.
Okay.
So the meetings?
I'll go.
Great.
Then I'll see you
Tuesday,
nine a.m. sharp.
[Pen scratching]
[Paper rustling]
[Chris Lancry
& Jacques Mercier's
"South of the Border" playing]
You want this?
I do.
♪
Take your time.
[Pad thuds]
[Indistinct conversations]
♪
[Silverware clinking]
Man: Enjoy.
♪
Yeah, you can sit
anywhere you want. That's fine.
♪
Abe, would you mind
watching my stuff?
♪
Hey.
Hello.
Nice day.
Are you
following me?
I'm sorry?
♪
Are you following me?
What are you, APD?
Know what?
Ithink
you're following me,
and if you're not gonna
identify yourselves,
then I'm calling in your plates
because I feel threatened.
[Engine starts]
Sorry
if we've disturbed you.
[Gearshift clicks]You have a nice day,
ma'am.
[Indistinct conversations]
[Slurps]
Oh, yeah. Yeah, please.
[Indistinct conversations]
[Cellphone buzzes and beeps]
[Headset beeps]
Saul Goodman,
speedy justice for you.
Uh, no, there's no charge
for the initial consultation.
Today?
Yeah, um...
I have an opening
around 3:30.
Oh, I'm working
out of my satellite office.
It's at Juan Tabo and Skyline.
I'm letting a nail salon
use the lobby,
so office is in back.
Great.
Uh, your name?
Dante.
See you then.
[Sighs]
[Cellphone buzzes and beeps][Headset beeps]
Saul Goodman,
speedy justice for you.
Yeah. Uh, yeah.
I do have an opening today...
Oh, hold on.
I'm getting another call.
Saul Goodman,
speedy justice for you.
Um, hold, please.
[Headset beeps]My apologies.
I'm [clears throat] having
a bit of a rush here today.
[Brakes squeal,
engine shuts off]
[Bells jingle]
You get these people out
right now.
What? These guys?
Are they bothering you?
Not them. Inside!
[I Campioni's
"La Vita E Colorata" playing]
[Indistinct conversations]
♪
Who's here to see
Saul Goodman?
You're him?
You're Saul?
Yeah.
♪
Then you're the guy,
right?
What guy's that?
Salamanca's guy.
♪
[Clears throat]
Yeah.
That's me.
[Clears throat]
Everybody who has
an appointment already...
Uh, oh, you know...
you know what?
Um...
[Sighs, clears throat]
Uh, Mr. "Spooge"?
It's just "Spooge."
Just Spooge.
Duly noted. Alright.
Um, Gael Morengo?
Okay.
Uh, let's see.
Is there a Dante?
Mm-hmm.
And Rocco Kubler.
Okay.
Everybody else, um,
kindly wait outside, alright?
Unless... Unless you desire
spa services while you wait.
Uh, that's a separate
charge, but it... it's
highly recommended.
The... The best pedicures
in Albuquerque,
right here.
[Chuckles]
Saul: Six.
Lucky number seven.
Oh, you're with him?
And eight.
Nice leathers.
Uh, okay, together.
And nine.
[Clears throat] Wow.
Um, thank you all
for your patience.
And... justice for all!
["Lacrima E Mare" playing]
[Bells jingle]Cucumber water
for paying customers only.
Oh, believe me,
they're gonna be paying.
"Spooge"!
♪
Oh, Spooge and friend.
Okay. Good. This way.
[Singing in Spanish]
Hi, ma'am.
[Beads clinking]
♪
Yeah, hang... hang a left
at the washing machine.
There you go.
I'll see you next week,
Rosa.
And it was nice meeting you,
Pilar.
Don't forget to bring as many
family members as you can.
We will.
Thank you, Ms. Wexler.
Take care.
[Teri Norton's
"Isle of Misery" playing]
[Doors closing]
♪
Shelby:
All done for today?
Yeah. Here you go.
Just keep it, Shelby.
Thanks, Kim.
See you tomorrow?
You bet.
♪
Mike: They're gone.
I'm sorry?
The two men
that were following you.
They're gone.
♪
Do I know you?
Would you mind
sitting for a moment?
And I will answer
any questions I can.
♪
I have men watching you
and your husband.
I'm not with the police,
and as far as I know,
they're not investigating
either of you.
I doknow that you've been
up to a few things
that you probably
would rather keep private.
I don't care.
That's not
what this is about.
I'm trying to solve
a problem of my own.
What problem?
♪
Lalo Salamanca.
Lalo Salamanca's dead.
♪
He...
isn't.
We're watching anyone
he might contact.
That includes you
and your husband.
Most likely,
he'll never reach out.
He's got bigger fish
to fry.
But in the thousand-to-one
chance that he does...
♪
And who do you
work for?
♪
I said I would answer
anything I can.
♪
You're the guy
from the desert.
♪
The one who was out there
with Jimmy.
♪
Why are you telling methis
and not him?
♪
Because I think you're made
of sterner stuff.
♪
Alright.
Now here's what's best
for everyone.
You spot my guys again,
which I'm hoping you won't,
let them go about
their business.
Just pretend
they're not there.
And pretty soon
they won't be.
You and your husband
just...
go on living your lives.
♪
I doknow you.
You worked in the parking booth
at the courthouse.
♪
You're the attendant.
I was.
♪
[Scoffs]
[Breathing shakily]
♪
[Clicking]
[Engine shuts off]
Hi...
[Children shouting playfully]
[Sighs]
♪
Man: The markets will continue
to be in a state of flux
until the Fed
tightens interest rates.
Some days we'll feel
pretty good about the rate
of economic recovery,
other days not so much.
Because of these macro issues.
The deficit, interest rates,
oil prices, what have you...
♪
[Sighs]
[Switch clicks]
♪
[Switches thudding, bolt clicks]
Mrs. Ryman:
I think I saw that somewhere.
Here!
Mrs. Ryman: Nope.
♪
How's youredge
coming along?
I'm still missing two...
Mr. Ryman: You found
all your edge pieces.
I thought I did.
Maybe we lost a few.
These trees
are killing me.
The pieces all look
exactly the same.
Then work on the cabin.I could.
♪
[Dog barking in distance]
[Sighs]
There was a green Ford van.
It was behind me
for almost three blocks.
A '98 Econoline.
We ran the plate.
Guy's a freelance plumber.
He's legit.
The man you placed
in my kitchen.
Roy.
You told me
that he had experience
as a short-order cook.
Two years at McDonald's
in college.
He's not there
just to make French fries.
I need guys in close.
He's not up to
Pollos standards.
I'll find
a replacement.
We're stretched thin.
I've got guys working
18-hour days all over town.
Two weeks.
We haven't had a tickle.
And?
All due respect,
the rest of the world thinks
the guy is dead.
Lalo Salamanca is alive.
[Exhales slowly]
Then where is he?
[Engine shuts off]
[Sighs]
[Footsteps approach]
Hey.
How was your day?
Uh,
what are we doing here?
Take a look.
What do you think?
About what?
My new office.
Potentially.
Come on.[Car alarm beeps]
[Sighs]
[Insects chirping]
Kim: Huh.
Mrs. Nguyen kicked me
to the curb.
What? Why?
It's a long story,
but upshot is
she wants me outta there
with extreme prejudice.
Wow.
Bad day, huh?
No.
It was a great day.
With actual
paying clients.
The word is out!
People are throwing
cash retainers at me...
just to say
Saul Goodman is their lawyer.
Because of
who you represented.
Well, I mean,
that's part of it.
But, um,
the bottom line is
I need a new place
to do business... pronto.
Now, this place
is a shithole,
but the price is right
and I think I can talk the
landlord into a month-to-month.
So it's temporary, you know,
'til I find something better.
[Sighs]
Hey.
What do you think?
It's small.
It's...dirty.
And this whole place
smells funny.
But the courthouse
is five blocks away.
You can't get to MDC
without driving past.
Parking is good,
bail bond row isn't far,
and, uh...
Taco Cabeza is just around
the corner.
Might be a diamond
in the rough.
Just promise me...
...you won't move
the toilet.
[Chuckles]
There it is.
Alright.
Um, speaking of
the Taco Cabeza...
I'm starving.
Let's do it.
[Vehicle passes]
On the next episode
of "Better Call Saul..."
Thank God he's dead.
I can put more guys
on the place
if that's what
you're thinking.
Open for business.
What you're doing to help the
little guy, it's incredible.
I'm just getting started.
I just need you
to know that I know.
It wasn't me, Cliff.
Sounds like money.
Okay. Great.
♪
Who is this Saul Goodman?
You?
You got it.
♪