[ELEVEN ECHOING] Goodbye, Mike.
[YELLING]
[SCREECHING]
[COUGHS]
[GROANS]
Mike?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Mike? Mike!
[SCREAMING] Mike!
Mike!
[WHIMPERS]
[SOLDIERS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[MUFFLED EXPLOSION]
[SOLDIER 1] Bravo team, check in.
[ELEVEN BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SOLDIERS CONVERSING INDISTINCTLY]
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
[KAREN] What about the Russians?
What if they come looking for her?
They don't know where she is.
And she can't contact
you without us knowing.
[MAN] The most important thing is for
you to try to go on with your lives
- and to keep all of this...
- Top secret. Yeah.
Understood. We're all
patriots in this house.
- [WOMAN] Go back to the beginning.
- [MIKE] I told you everything.
- I understand this is difficult, Michael.
- I don't know where she is.
And even if I did, I'd never tell you.
I would never tell you.
[WOMAN] I know it's difficult to accept,
the stories she told you were not true.
She's a very dangerous individual.
[MAN] If she contacts
you, you must tell us.
[WOMAN] Otherwise, you're putting
yourself and your entire family at risk.
Do you understand, Michael?
Do you understand?
[MAN] Michael?
Michael?
[MAN] Fan out.
Somebody check the left side,
I'll check the right side.
[HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING]
[MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
_
[HOPPER] Oh, Jesus!
[ELEVEN] Ghost.
Yeah, I see that.
- [ELEVEN] Halloween.
- Sure is.
But right now, it's breakfast,
okay? Come on, let's eat.
They wouldn't see me.
- Who wouldn’t see you?
- The bad men.
What are you talking about?
Trick or treat.
You want to go trick-or-treating?
You know the rules.
- Yes, but...
- Yeah, so you know the answer.
- No, but they wouldn't see me.
- No. Hey. I don't care.
- But they wouldn’t see me.
- I don't care, all right?
You go out there, ghost
or not, it's a risk.
We don't take risks. All right?
They're stupid, and...
We're not stupid!
Exactly.
Now, you take that off, sit down
and eat. Your food's getting cold.
[SIGHS] All right, look...
How about I get off early tonight,
and I buy us a bunch of candy,
and we can sit around and get fat,
and we watch a scary movie together?
How's that for a compromise?
[STUTTERS] "Compromise"?
C-O-M-promise. Compromise.
How about that's your
word for the day? Yeah?
It's something that's kinda
in-between. It's like halfway happy.
By 5-1-5?
5:15. Yeah, sure.
Promise?
Yes.
I promise.
Halfway happy.
[CHUCKLES]
Will?
Come on, honey, up and at 'em.
- Jonathan?
- Yeah?
Where's Will?
- What?
- Where's Will?
- He's not in his room?
- No.
Uh...
Will?
What are you doing?
Peeing?
[CHUCKLES] Okay.
[TOILET FLUSHES]
Okay.
- Let's get this... on.
- [GRUNTS]
Oh!
You need some tape. Hold on.
What's this?
Nothing.
Did you have another episode?
No, it's just, um... a sketch
for a story I'm writing.
[JOYCE SIGHS] All right.
[JONATHAN] Three, two, one...
- ["GHOSTBUSTERS" PLAYING]
- Great. Hold up the proton blaster.
All right, now turn to the light.
Oh! I want to see those pearls. Yeah!
- [MEOWS]
- Who you gonna call?
[SCATTING]
[LAUGHS] Oh!
Adorable, baby. Just adorable!
- God. You are such a nerd.
- Shut up.
No wonder you only hang out with boys.
- Erica!
- Just the facts.
[MOUTHING] Nerd.
[MRS. SINCLAIR] My God, I
love this costume. Keep it up.
[MIKE] All right, that's the last one.
No, just one more. Come on, please?
Ah!
- Can I go to school?
- Wait, wait.
- Okay, say, "Who you gonna call?"
- No!
[ALL SINGING "GHOSTBUSTERS"]
- ♪ Who you gonna call? ♪
- ♪ Ghostbusters! ♪
Hey, Spengler!
- Egon! Yeah!
- Venkman!
Whoa! Whoa!
- What?
- Why are you Venkman?
- Because I'm Venkman.
- No, I'm Venkman.
Why can't there be two Venkmans?
Because there's only one Venkman in
real life. We planned this months ago.
I'm Venkman, Dustin's Stantz,
you're Egon, and you're Winston.
- I specifically didn't agree to Winston.
- Yes, you did!
- I don't think he did.
- No one wants to be Winston, man.
What's wrong with Winston?
He joined the team super late,
he's not funny, and he's
not even a scientist!
- Yeah, but he's still cool.
- If he's cool, then you be Winston.
- I can't!
- Why not?
- [STUTTERS] Because...
- [MOCKING MIKE] Because you're not black?
- I didn't say that!
- You thought it.
- Mike!
Guys... Guys! Guys!
Why is no one else wearing costumes?
[SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
Crap.
- [STUDENTS LAUGHING]
- [STUDENT] Oh, my God!
When do people make these decisions?
[WILL] Everyone dressed up last year.
- It's a conspiracy, I'm telling you.
- Just be cool.
[BOY] Who you gonna call? The nerds!
- We gonna do this?
- Not right now. We look like morons.
[DUSTIN] Maybe she likes Ghostbusters?
Of course she likes Ghostbusters,
but that's not the point.
The point is we're
dressed up and she isn't.
[DUSTIN] I didn't bring
regular clothes. You?
[LUCAS] No.
Then we have no choice. We
gotta do this. It's now or never.
- Right. [SNIFFS]
- Let's engage.
We could ask her after class.
- Yup.
- Okay.
[JOYCE] See? It's an exact match.
- But... why would he lie to me?
- [INHALES DEEPLY] He's a kid, Joyce.
I mean, you heard him
describe these episodes.
It's not like he's describing a nightmare.
He talks about them like they're real.
Yeah, because they're not
nightmares, they're flashbacks.
I know a couple guys who
have had these things,
and it feels like you're
there, like it's happening.
- Then what the hell is this?
- Owens said it would get worse.
- That place...
- What do you wanna do?
You wanna take him back to Chicago?
Well, there's that guy in
Boston that's supposed to be...
They're all a bunch of quacks.
They'll all tell you the same
thing, just cost you more money.
I think he's right... about trauma.
And we're coming up on a year, you know.
I think everybody's on edge.
Me, you... Will most of all.
I think we just gotta get
through the next few weeks.
[SIGHS]
Nothing's gonna go back
to the way that it was.
Not really.
But it'll get better.
In time.
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
[JOYCE MUMBLES]
- Here.
- Thank you.
- [CHOKES AND COUGHS]
- [CHUCKLES]
Jesus! Hopper...
Brings me back to old times.
What?
- [SIGHS] Sharing my cigarettes between...
- Fifth and sixth period.
Yeah, under the steps.
Mr. Cooper caught us
that time, remember?
He was like, [GRUFFLY] "Hey, assholes."
We ran. We just ran.
[CHUCKLES]
God, I want this to be over.
I know.
[JOYCE SNIFFLES]
[BEEPS]
[STATIC CRACKLING]
How's it looking out there, cowboy?
[MAN] Uh, you know, Doc. The usual.
Nice and nasty with a
chance of radioactivity.
Oh, yeah, it's barbecued
all right. Anyone hungry?
[TECHNICIAN] And...
[BEEPING]
we're back on!
[CHEERING AND APPLAUDING]
[WILL] There was this storm.
[OWENS] Okay. So how did you
feel when you saw the storm?
[WILL] I felt frozen.
[OWENS] Actually frozen? Cold?
[WILL] No, like how you
feel when you're scared,
and you can't breathe
or talk or do anything.
I felt... I felt this evil...
[BARBARA ECHOING]
Nancy, this isn't you.
[NANCY] Barb, just go
ahead and go home, okay?
[BARBARA] Nancy?
Nancy!
Nancy.
What's going on? Are you okay?
- I can't keep doing this.
- Doing what?
- Pretending like everything's okay.
- What are you talking about?
Barbara.
It's like everyone forgot.
It's like nobody cares.
Except her parents.
- And now they're selling their house.
- Nance...
And they're going to spend the
rest of their lives looking for her.
- I know.
- It's destroying them.
I know. Okay? I get it. But listen,
there's nothing we can do about it.
Yeah, we could tell them the truth.
Well, you know that we can't do that.
We don't have to tell them everything.
This isn't some game, Nance. If
they found out that we told any...
They could put us in jail. Okay?
Or worse, they could destroy our families.
They could do anything they want. Okay?
Just think about what you're saying.
Hey...
Hey, hey...
Hey, it's... [SIGHS]
It's hard, but let's...
let's just go to Tina's stupid party...
wear our stupid costumes
that we've been working on
for a stupid amount of time,
and just pretend like we're
stupid teenagers, okay?
Can we just do that, just for tonight?
Okay.
Come here.
[NANCY SIGHS]
[RINGING]
[DUSTIN CLEARS THROAT] Um...
Hi, Max. I'm Dustin, and this is...
- Lucas.
- Yeah, I know.
The stalkers.
[STUTTERS] Uh, no. Actually...
We weren't stalking you.
No, we were just concerned because,
you know, you're new and all.
Yeah, for your safety.
Mmm-hmm. There are a
lot of bullies here.
- [STUTTERING] So many bullies, it's crazy.
- Yeah.
Is that why you're wearing proton packs?
Well, these don't function. But...
I do have this handy-dandy
little trap here.
And look, it even opens and
closes. Look, look, look...
Voilà! [CHUCKLES]
It's cool, right?
No? Okay. But, um...
So, we were talking last
night, and you're new here,
so you probably don't have any
friends to take you trick-or-treating,
and you're scared of
bullies, so we were thinking
that it would be okay
if you come with us.
- "It'd be okay"?
- Yeah. Our party's a democracy,
the majority voted you could come.
Didn't realize it was such an honor
to go trick-or-treating with you.
We know where to get the
full-sized candy bars.
We figured you'd want in.
That's presumptuous of you.
Yeah. Totally. Uh,
so, um... you'll come?
We're meeting at the Maple
Street cul-de-sac at 7:00.
That's 7:00 on the dot!
"Presumptuous."
That's a good thing, right?
[SIGHS]
Is it bad?
Lucas, is it bad? Lucas? Son
of a bitch, Lucas. Is it bad?
[WOMAN ON TV] How does it feel?
Like pouring pure silk onto my skin.
[MAN] Inhuman. Relentless.
Arnold Schwarzenegger is... The Term...
Well, I'm stunned. I
don't know what to think.
- [MAN] Don't you love me?
- [ERICA] Of course I love you.
It's just that it's so sudden.
I mean, it's not like you.
Erica, I am this way because of you.
- [ERICA] Me?
- "Me?"
[MAN] Mmm-hmm.
You have made me wild and impetuous,
- just like you.
- "Impetuous."
People are going to be aghast.
- "People are going to be aghast."
- [MAN LAUGHS] They're gonna love it.
[BOTH LAUGHING ON TV]
I mean, it's gonna stun the
whole town. The whole world!
Erica, tell me that you will marry
me, in this house, tonight...
[TELEVISION CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY]
[CHITTERING]
[TWIG SNAPS]
Hey.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
What's your name?
What're you doing out here in the cold?
[GRUNTS]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[FLIES BUZZING]
So, you're telling me that
Merrill poisoned your farm,
because he thinks you poisoned
his, which, of course, you didn't?
No, sir. And I got me an
alibi the night he accuses me.
My Jenny and her boys were in
town. I was with them all night.
- Did you actually see Merrill?
- No need. That man done lost his mind.
Went around slandering me,
threatening all sorts of madness.
- A pumpkin conspiracy.
- [CHUCKLES]
Hawkins' very own Chinatown.
Merrill threatening to do something
and him actually doing something
are two very different things.
- You got a better explanation?
- Cold weather.
- It's October.
- Yeah, it's a cold one.
- You see these hands?
- Yeah.
- You know why they look like that?
- Because you're old?
- You're damn straight.
- [POWELL CHUCKLES]
And I've been doing this a
long time, Chief. A long time.
And I ain't never seen
anything the likes of this.
- None of us have.
- None of us?
Merrill didn't just hit me last
night. He hit damn near everyone.
What are you talking about?
Jack O'Dell, Pete Freeling,
Rick Neary, the Christensens.
All of their crops, dead.
Give me those names again.
You're late again.
- Yeah, I had to get catch-up homework.
- Jesus. I don't care.
You're late again, and
you're skating home.
Do you hear me?
["WANGO TANGO" BY TED NUGENT PLAYING]
- [SONG CONTINUES ON CAR RADIO]
- God, this place is such a shithole.
- It's not that bad.
- No?
[BILLY INHALES DEEPLY] Mmm!
You smell that, Max?
That's actually shit.
- Cow shit.
- I don't see any cows.
Clearly, you haven't met
the high-school girls.
- [SCOFFS] So what, you like it here now?
- No.
- Then why are you defending it?
- I'm not.
Sure sounds like it.
- It's just we're stuck here, so...
- Hmm.
You're right. We're stuck here.
And whose fault is that?
Yours.
- What'd you say?
- Nothing.
- Did you say it's my fault?
- No.
You know whose fault it is.
Say it.
Max...
say it.
Say it!
["WANGO TANGO" CONTINUES PLAYING]
Really, everyone dressed up last year.
Billy, slow down.
- Oh, these your new hick friends?
- No! I don't know them.
I guess you won't care
if I hit 'em, then?
I get bonus points, I
get 'em all in one go?
No, Billy, stop. It's not funny.
[REVVING]
Hey, guys?
Billy, come on, stop
it. It's not funny. Stop!
- Go!
- Mike, you need to haul ass!
- Billy, stop it!
- [TIRES SCREECHES]
[DUSTIN] Whoa! Shit! Shit! Shit! Shit!
Yeah! That was a close one, huh?
[BILLY LAUGHS]
[DUSTIN] Holy shit!
Was that...
Mad Max.
["WANGO TANGO" CONTINUES PLAYING]
[WIND CHIMES RATTLING]
[FLIES BUZZING]
Now, you tryin' to tell me, with
a straight face, cold did this?
How far does it go?
[POWELL OVER RADIO]
Hey, Chief, you copy?
[HOPPER] Uh...
Hey, Chief.
[HOPPER] How's it looking over there?
Like a giant pissed all
over Jack's bean field.
Smells, too. It smell over there?
Uh, yeah, little bit.
[GRUNTS] Smells like
a nursing home, man.
Listen. I want you guys to track
the rot, see how far it goes.
Just, uh, mark anything that's dead.
- That's gonna take some time.
- So take it.
And, look, we don't know what
caused this. Could be poison.
So don't touch anything without gloves.
[SNIFFS]
Copy that, Chief.
[SIGHS]
You got any marking flags?
So you hit "T" to zoom
in, and "W" zooms back out.
See? Easy-peasy.
Just make sure to turn off
the power to save energy there.
Listen. Stay close
to your brother, okay?
And listen, listen, listen...
If you get a bad feeling or anything,
you tell him to take you straight home.
- You promise?
- Okay.
- Are you ready, bud?
- Yeah.
Be safe.
[IMITATING DRACULA]
I hope it doesn't suck!
- [SNICKERS]
- [CHUCKLES]
[JONATHAN] I just don't
get what she sees in him.
What?
Bob.
At least he doesn't treat me different.
I mean, I can't even go
trick-or-treating by myself. It's lame.
What? You think I'm lame?
No, but it's not like Nancy's
coming to watch over Mike, you know?
[SIGHS]
[DUSTIN] Will! Hey!
[CAR HORN HONKS]
[DUSTIN] Hey, don't cross the
streams. Don't cross the streams!
[SIGHS]
Hey, listen.
Yeah?
If I let you go on your own, you
promise to stay in the neighborhood?
- Yeah! Yeah, yeah, totally.
- And be back at Mike's by 9:00.
- 9:30?
- 9:00.
- Yeah.
- Deal?
- Yeah, deal.
- All right.
Hey, Will. Don't let any of your
spazzy friends use this, all right?
Okay.
[IMITATING DRACULA]
I hope it doesn't suck.
[WILL CHUCKLES]
[LUCAS] Will!
- Egon!
- Yeah! You ready for tonight, man?
Awesome!
["SHOUT AT THE DEVIL"
BY MÖTLEY CRÜE PLAYING]
[ALL] ...thirty-eight, thirty-nine,
forty, forty-one, forty-two!
[ALL CHEERING LOUDLY]
- Yeah!
- Forty-two!
We got ourselves a new Keg King!
- [CHANTING] Billy! Billy! Billy!
- That's how you do it, Hawkins!
Billy! Billy! Billy!
[CHANTING CONTINUES]
We got ourselves a new
Keg King, Harrington.
- Yeah, that's right!
- Yeah. Eat it, Harrington.
What's in this?
Pure fuel! Pure fuel!
Whoo!
[BURPS]
[GLASSES SHATTERING]
Hey... Whoa, whoa! Hey...
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Take it easy.
Take it easy. Nance, Nance, Nance...
We're just being stupid teenagers
for the night. Wasn't that the deal?
["ISLANDS IN THE STREAM" BY DOLLY
PARTON AND KENNY ROGERS PLAYING]
[CHUCKLES] Yeah.
[JOYCE CHUCKLING]
- No. No, no.
- Come on. Yes.
- Yes. Yes. Yes. Come on.
- No. No. No. [LAUGHING]
Oh, there it is. [CHUCKLES]
You playing Frankenstein to my Dracula?
- Come on, you're stiff as a board. Relax.
- I'm sorry. It's...
He's fine. Okay? Jonathan's with him.
[SIGHS] I know.
It's just every time he's away
from me, it's like I can't function.
- I know it sounds silly.
- No, it's not silly. It's not silly.
What if we were to move
out of Hawkins... together?
- What?
- I know.
Whoa, Nellie, right? No, I just...
I've been thinking about what you said.
About how we've got
all these memories here,
and you wish you had
enough money to move.
Well, my parents are
selling their house in Maine.
There's a RadioShack nearby.
I'm sure they'd take me on.
We could just...
- My turn to be silly now.
- [SIGHS] Bob...
No, it's fine. Wine makes me crazy.
Oh, it's just so hard to explain.
It's just this... This
is not a normal family.
It could be.
♪ Everything is nothing
If you got no one ♪
♪ And you just walk in the night ♪
♪ Slowly losing sight of the real thing ♪
[DOORBELL RINGS]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Finally.
Huh?
[IMITATES DRACULA] Victims.
[KNOCKING AND RINGING CONTINUES]
[ALL] Trick or treat!
[CHUCKLES] Oh!
Well, aren't you cute?
The little exterminators.
[LUCAS SIGHS] If I get another 3
Musketeers, I'm gonna kill myself.
- What's wrong with 3 Musketeers?
- "What's wrong with 3 Musketeers?"
- No one likes 3 Musketeers.
- Yeah, it's just nougat.
Whoa. "Just nougat"?
Just nougat? It is top three for me.
- Top three?
- Top three!
Oh, God. Give me a break.
Seriously, I can just eat a
whole bowl of nougat. Straight up.
- [GROWLING]
- [BOYS SCREAM]
[LUCAS SQUEALS]
[CHUCKLING]
Holy shit! You should have
seen the look on your faces.
And you? Who screams like that?
You sound like a little girl.
Hey, you guys coming or not? Oh,
I heard we should hit up Loch Nora.
That's where the rich people
live, right? [CHUCKLES]
[BOTH] Yeah!
[SIGHS]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [HOPPER GASPS AND SIGHS]
You're dead.
Yeah, you got me, kid.
[TOY GUN FIRING]
- [KID CHUCKLES]
- Happy Halloween.
Oh, shit, shit, shit,
shit, shit, shit, shit.
[GROANS]
Hey, kid. Give me some
of that candy, would you?
No way.
All right. How about now?
Who are you? I'm Maria.
Will you play with me?
Would you like one of my flowers?
[BEEPING]
L...
A...
T...
E.
Late.
[CONTINUES BEEPING]
["MONSTER MASH" PLAYING]
♪ He did the mash ♪
- ♪ He did the monster mash ♪
- ♪ The monster mash ♪
- ♪ It was a graveyard smash ♪
- ♪ He did the mash... ♪
Another full-size. Like, seriously,
rich people are such suckers.
- Wait. You're not rich, right?
- No, I live up Old Cherry Road.
Oh.
No, it's fine. I mean, the
street's good for skating.
[DUSTIN] Hmm.
Yeah, totally tubular.
What? Did I say that right?
Or is it, like, tubular.
It's, like, [IMITATES
SURFER] totally tubular.
- Totally tubular!
- What a gnarly wave, dude.
- Totally brodacious, bro!
- [MAX] Stop. My ears are hurting.
[DUSTIN AND LUCAS CONTINUE INDISTINCTLY]
- Did you agree to this?
- What?
To her joining our party.
- It's just for Halloween.
- You should have checked with me.
Well, they were excited. I guess
I thought you'd be okay with it.
She's ruining the
best night of the year.
- Watch it, Zombie Boy.
- [GASPS]
Trick or treat, freak.
- Boo!
- [GASPS]
[AMBIENT RUMBLING]
[ECHOING] Mike?
Mike?
Mike!
[CHITTERING]
[CHITTERING CONTINUES]
[OMINOUS LOUD RUMBLING]
[LOUD GROWLING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [MIKE] Will!
- [SCREAMS]
- Will, what's wrong?
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
I couldn't find you. Are you hurt?
Holy shit!
- [LUCAS] Is he okay?
- I don't know.
I'm gonna get you home, okay?
I'm gonna get you home. Hold on.
- All right, take it easy.
- I got him.
Mike?
Keep trick-or-treating.
I'm bored anyways.
What's wrong with him?
["GIRLS ON FILM" BY DURAN DURAN PLAYING]
[RETCHING]
["GIRLS ON FILM" CONTINUES PLAYING]
[GIRL] Nice costume.
- Huh?
- Nice costume.
Oh, uh, yeah. I'm going
as a guy who hates parties.
[CHUCKLES]
- I'm Samantha.
- Uh, Jonathan.
Kiss?
The band.
[CHUCKLES]
- No, no, no.
- Get off.
- No, you've had enough, okay?
- Screw you!
Nance, I'm serious. Hey. Hey.
Hey. Stop. No, I'm serious.
- Put it down.
- No!
- Nance, put it down.
- Steve! Stop.
- Stop. Stop.
- [GASPS]
[ALL EXCLAIM]
What the hell?
Nance.
Nance, I'm sorry.
- That's not coming off, Nance.
- It's coming.
Come on. Let me just take
you home, okay? Come here.
- Let me take you home. Come on.
- [SLURRING] You wanted this.
No, I didn't want this. I
told you to stop drinking.
- It's bullshit. Bullshit.
- No, it's not bullshit. Okay?
- No, it's not bullshit, Nancy.
- No, you. You're bullshit.
[STAMMERS] What?
You're pretending like
everything is okay.
You know, like we didn't...
like we didn't kill Barb.
Like, it's great. Like, we're
in love and we're partying.
Yeah, let's party, huh?
Party. We're partying.
This is bullshit.
"Like we're in love"?
[STEVE SHUDDERS]
It's bullshit.
You don't love me?
[SIGHS]
[WILL] It's like... like I'm stuck.
[MIKE] Like, like, stuck in the Upside Down?
[WILL SIGHS] No.
You know on a View-Master,
when it gets, like...
- Caught between two slides?
- Yeah. Like that.
Like one side's our
world, and the other...
The other slide is the Upside Down.
And...
And there was this noise
coming from everywhere.
And then I saw something.
- The Demogorgon?
- No.
It was like this huge shadow in the sky.
Only, it was alive.
And it was coming for me.
Is this all real?
Or is it like the doctors
say, all in your head?
I don't know. Just...
Just please don't tell the others, okay?
They won't understand.
Eleven would.
She would?
Yeah.
She always did.
Sometimes I feel like I still see her.
Like she's still
around, but she never is.
I don't know. Sometimes I
feel like I'm going crazy.
Me, too.
Hey, well, if we're both going crazy,
then we'll go crazy together, right?
[CHUCKLES] Yeah. Crazy together.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[NANCY EXHALES]
[SIGHS]
Jonathan?
[KNOCKING RHYTHMICALLY]
Hey, kid. Open up, all
right? Look, I know I'm late.
I got candy here, all right?
I got all the good stuff.
Please, will you open the door?
I'm gonna freeze to death out here.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[TV PLAYING IN DISTANCE]
Hey, kid. Open up, would you?
I got, uh... stuck somewhere,
and I lost track of time.
And I'm sorry.
El, would you please open the door?
El?
[SIGHS]
All right.
I'm just gonna be out here by
myself, eating all this candy.
I'm gonna get fat.
It's very unhealthy
to leave me out here.
Could have a heart attack or something.
But, you know, you do what you want.
[ANNOUNCER ON TV] One quarter
pound of all-American beef,
fresh-cut tomato, and four
strips of crispy bacon.
[MAN AND WOMAN] Did somebody say bacon?
- [SWITCHES CHANNELS]
- [MAN] Refreshing lemon...
[WOMAN] ...and they're
perfect for dunking. Mmm!
[VOICES ECHOING]
[MIKE ECHOING] It's day 353.
I had a bad day today.
I don't know. I...
I guess I wish you were here.
I mean, we all do.
If you're out there, just
please give me a sign.
Mike.
Eleven?
[SOBBING]
[DUSTIN] Tubular.
Tubular.
[CHIRPING AND GROWLING]
Mews, is that...
[LOUD THUD]
[NOISE CONTINUES]
Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit.
[SCREAMS]
[CHITTERING]
Holy sh...
["GHOSTBUSTERS" PLAYING]
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ If there's something strange
In your neighborhood ♪
♪ Who you gonna call? ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ If there's something weird
And it don't look good ♪
♪ Who you gonna call? ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ I ain't afraid of no ghost ♪
♪ If you're seeing things
Running through your head ♪
♪ Who can you call? ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ An invisible man
Sleeping in your bed ♪
♪ Oh! Who you gonna call? ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ I ain't afraid of no ghost ♪
♪ Don't get caught alone Oh, no ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ When it comes through your door ♪
♪ Unless you just want some more ♪
♪ I think you better call ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ Who you gonna call? ♪