[LINE RINGING]
[CREAKING]
[HOPPER] Hey, you reached Jim.
I'm probably doing something
incredible right now,
and I can't...
[SIGHS]
[WILL] It's like... It's like I feel
what the shadow monster's feeling.
See what he's seeing.
Like in the Upside Down?
Some of him is there.
But some of him is here, too.
- Here, like, in this house?
- In this house and...
in me.
It's like... It's like he's reaching
into Hawkins more and more.
And the more he spreads, the
more connected to him I feel.
And the more you see these now-memories.
At first I just felt it
in the back of my head.
I didn't even really know it was there.
It's like when you have a dream
and you can't remember it
unless you think really hard.
It was like that.
But know it's like...
Now I remember. I remember all the time.
Maybe...
- Maybe that's good.
- Good?
Just think about it, Will.
You're like a spy now. A superspy.
Spying on the shadow monster.
If you know what he's
seeing and feeling...
maybe that's how we can stop him.
Maybe all of this is
happening for a reason.
- You really think so?
- Yeah. Yeah, I really do.
What if he figures out
we're spying on him?
- [SNIFFLES] What if he spies back?
- He won't.
How do you know?
We won't let him.
[HOPPER BREATHING HEAVILY]
Ugh!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [SCREECHING]
- [CONTINUES BREATHING HEAVILY]
[HISSING]
[SPITS]
[HOPPER COUGHING]
[CONTINUES COUGHING]
Ugh!
[GRUNTING AND COUGHING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
synced & corrected by PopcornAWH
www.addic7ed.com
- [MAN 1] Hey.
- [MAN 2] Hey. Did you get 'em?
[MAN 1] Yeah.
[BOTH CONTINUE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[SONG PLAYING ON STEREO]
We'd like a... uh, a room.
We got those.
You want a single or a double?
[BOTH] Double.
[SLURPING]
Nance...
- Uh, on or off?
- Hmm.
- What?
- Nothing. Just...
déjà vu.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
- Yeah.
- [BOTH CHUCKLE SOFTLY]
Don't you think it's weird?
What?
How we only seem to hang out
when the world's about to end?
It's not going to end.
Feels like it. [SIGHS]
Still have yours?
- [JONATHAN] Yeah.
- Mmm...
- Yeah, mine's bigger.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
[SIGHS]
What happened?
What do you mean?
To us?
After everything, you just...
disappeared.
[SIGHS]
Yeah, Will needed me.
And Steve...
I waited.
Yeah, like, only a month.
[NANCY] I want them off.
[GASPING]
Will, what's wrong?
[WILL] Mom?
Mom?
- Mom?
- [GASPS] Yeah?
- I saw him.
- You saw who, baby?
Hopper.
I think he's in trouble.
I think he's going to die.
[GASPING]
[GRUNTING]
[RETCHES]
[PANTING]
Shit!
[CONTINUES PANTING]
[THUD]
[SONG PLAYING ON STEREO]
- That's enough, Erica.
- Uh-uh.
- Dad?
- Mmm-hmm?
When Mom's mad at you, how
do you make her not mad?
Hmm. That's a great question.
How do you, hon?
[MR. SINCLAIR] First, I apologize.
Then, I get your mother
whatever she wants.
Even when she's wrong?
She's never wrong, son.
That's right. [CHUCKLES]
- Not hungry?
- [LUCAS] Not really.
Where you goin'?
To hang out with Dustin.
[SOFTLY] Sorry.
[CLAUDIA] Mews!
Mewsy!
Mews!
Dusty, baby, you're sure
she's not in your room?
- [SIGHS]
- Uh-huh.
[AUTOMATED VOICE] If you'd
like to make a call...
Thank you so much, Mr. McCorkle.
Thank you so much.
You are a true lifesaver.
- All right, this was great.
- [DIAL TONE]
Thank you. All right. Have a good one.
Bye-bye, now. All right. You, too.
All right, great news.
They found her?
No. But they saw her
wandering around Loch Nora.
[CRYING] How did the poor baby
get all the way out there?
I don't know. Lost, I guess. But
they're gonna look for her.
And I'll stay here, just
in case they call again.
And you're gonna go help look?
Yeah? Yeah?
Give me hug. Give me a hug. Go get her.
- You're gonna find her.
- Okay.
- We can find her.
I love you.
- I love you.
- All right, go.
All right.
All right, Dart. Breakfast time.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit.
Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit.
Shit. Shit. Shit.
[PANTING]
Come on. Come on, I know you're hungry.
- Yes. Yes, yes, yes.
- [DART GROWLING]
Yes.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
[DUSTIN PANTING]
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
[DART GROWLS]
Shit!
[DUSTIN BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[CHITTERING]
[YELLING]
[SCREECHING]
- [YELLING]
- [DART GROWLING]
[GRUNTING]
- I'm sorry. You ate my cat.
- [DART SCREECHING]
- [BRAKES SQUEALING]
- [MAN] All right. I think this is it.
- Five-one-five Larrabee, right?
- [SONG PLAYING ON STEREO]
Yes.
Five-fifteen.
All right, "Five-fifteen." Sure.
Thank you.
Hey.
You apologize to your mama, yeah? Huh?
Must be scared half to death.
How long's it been?
Long time.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SIGHS]
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
[BECKY] Go away! I'm not interested!
Look, I don't want your
Thin Mints, all right, kid?
- Thin Mints?
- Or your religious mumbo jumbo.
Whatever you're selling,
I ain't buying, okay?
[CREAKING]
I want to see Mama.
Name a way you occupy your time
when you're having a boring day at work.
[BUZZER RINGS]
- [MAN] Drink coffee.
- [HOST] "Drink coffee," said Mike.
- [BELL DINGS]
- Yeah! Five answers will beat it, Lynn.
[LYNN] Visit with other employees.
- [HOST] "Visit with other employees."
- Rainbow.
- [BELL DINGS]
- [APPLAUSE]
- Three to the right. Four to the left.
- Mama?
Breathe. Sunflower.
Rainbow.
- Three to the right. Four to the left.
- Mama, can you hear me?
Four-fifty. Breathe.
Sunflower.
Rainbow.
Mama? It's me...
Jane.
I'm here now.
Breathe. Sunflower. Rainbow. Four-fifty.
Breathe. Sunflower.
- What's wrong with Mama?
- Rainbow.
- Four-fifty.
- [CRYING]
[ROCK SONG PLAYING ON STEREO]
[SONG STOPS]
[JONATHAN] Are you positive
this is the right place?
"3833." Yeah.
All right.
[TRAIN HORN BLARING IN THE DISTANCE]
[BUZZES]
[MURRAY] Look at the camera.
- The camera.
- [JONATHAN] What camera?
[MURRAY] Not the loudspeaker.
Above you, to the right.
[DOOR RATTLES]
Nancy Wheeler. Jonathan Byers.
You two are a long way from home.
Well...
I hope you didn't come all this
way to tell me about the bear
in the Harrington kid's backyard.
I've heard that one already.
Take a look. Go ahead, don't be shy.
I followed up on 200 tips,
most bogus, but that's how
these things always go, okay?
I know every last step
Barbara took that day,
every last person she talked to.
The answer to what happened
to your friend, it's up here somewhere.
I assure you that. I just
gotta connect the right dots.
Timeline's wrong.
I'm sorry?
Your timeline is wrong.
And the girl with the buzzed hair,
she's not Russian. She's
from Hawkins Lab.
Her name was Eleven.
You might wanna sit down for this.
- [ROCK SONG PLAYING ON STEREO]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
If you're not out in an hour...
Walking home. Yeah, yeah, I know.
Hey! Watch the attitude, shitbird.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- [VIDEO GAMES BEEPING]
Sorry about that, Road Warrior.
What happened?
Short circuit in the motherboard.
A real bummer.
But fret not. I got another machine
up and running in the back.
Hold these.
You better get me that
date now, Sinclair.
- I told you I would.
- [GRUNTS]
And keep things PG in here, all right?
[DOOR CLOSES]
What is this shit, stalker?
Sorry. I just needed a safe place.
A safe place to what? Be creepy?
Listen. I'm gonna tell you the truth
about everything that
happened last year.
But if anyone finds out,
you could be arrested.
[SIGHS] Possibly killed.
- Killed?
- I need to know.
Do you accept the risk?
- Oh, my God! This... this is so stupid.
- Do you accept the risk?
Yeah.
Sure. Fine.
I accept the risk.
Let's hear it.
Last year...
Will didn't get lost in the woods.
He got lost somewhere else.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Hey, is this where you saw him?
[STUTTERS] Is this where you saw Hopper?
I think so. Yeah.
[SOFTLY] Okay.
[MIKE] Here!
Okay, so... so Hopper is here?
Yeah. Now we just need to find
out where here is, right?
Right.
Did he say anything? I
mean, before he left?
[SIGHS] Uh, some...
something about vines?
- [CAR APPROACHING]
- Hopper.
Surprise.
I would've called, but you
said not to clog up the line.
You know, I... We're fine,
we don't need anything.
When I was sick as a kid, and I
was sick all the time as a kid,
nothing made me feel better than
focusing on these brain teasers.
Those are great. Ah...
I could teach him how to play.
- You know, he's sleeping.
- [THUNDER RUMBLING]
Okay.
I could wait with you?
[SIGHS] Listen, it's
just not a good time.
But, um, you know what?
I'll call you, okay?
Thank you.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Well, have him call me. They don't
call me Bob the Brain for nothing.
[CHUCKLES]
[GASPS] Bob!
That's my name.
Huh.
Hmm.
- You drew all these yourself?
- [JOYCE] Mmm-hmm.
- Why, exactly?
- I... I told you the rules.
- No questions, okay?
- Yeah.
We... we just need you to
help us figure out what...
Bob? Bob?
Over here.
Where... where this is.
That's the objective. Find the X.
Yeah? What's at the X? Pirate treasure?
[CHUCKLES]
Bob, no questions.
Okay.
- [SIGHS AND CLICKS TONGUE]
- [JOYCE CLEARS THROAT]
Let me talk to you for a second.
Hang on, guys.
Joyce, you can talk to me.
You know that, right?
[STAMMERS] Yeah. What's
the problem, exactly?
What's the problem?
Joyce, [SIGHS] Will doesn't look well.
You don't look well.
What's going on?
Nothing. Nothing.
Is this an episode? Is this
one of Will's episodes?
No. No! No. [SCOFFS]
[STUTTERS] I'm sorry. I just...
I don't...
see how any of this is
good for Will, or for you.
And even if I wanted to play along,
I mean, how could I figure anything out
if I don't understand the
context of the game?
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
- Or...
- What?
- What is it?
- I know that shape.
It's Lovers' Lake.
It's Lovers' Lake. I get it.
Okay, I get. That's Lake Jordan.
And if that's Lake Jordan,
then you can probably find...
Yeah, that's, uh, Sattler's quarry.
And if you just follow it naturally...
it moves to...
the Eno River.
And there it is. That's
the Eno, do you see it?
Okay, so the lines aren't roads.
But they act like roads.
And they act like roads 'cause
when you follow 'em, you'll see...
they don't go over water.
And that's the giveaway.
That's the giveaway. Ha!
Don't you get it? It's not a puzzle,
it's a map.
It's a map of Hawkins.
[BOB LAUGHS]
Right, Will?
[SQUEALING]
[RADIO STATIC]
[HOPPER] Does anybody copy?
Look, if anybody copies, this is
Jim Hopper, Hawkins' Chief...
[RADIO STATIC]
[PANTING]
[HOPPER GASPS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SCREECHING]
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[CONTINUES GRUNTING]
Guys, this is Dustin again.
Does anyone copy? This is a code red.
I repeat, a code red!
I really need someone to pick up here.
Hopper's MIA, and I've got a code red.
Code red!
All right, it's Dustin again.
Seriously, I have a code red.
Could you please shut up?
Erica? Erica, is Lucas there?
- Where is he?
- Don’t know. Don't care.
[STUTTERS] Is he with Mike?
Like I said, I don't
know and I don't care.
Please tell him it's super important.
Please tell him that I have a code...
Code red?
- Yep, code red. Exactly.
- Mmm-hmm.
I got a code for you instead.
It's called code shut-your-mouth.
[RADIO STATIC]
[STUTTERS] Erica?
[BECKY] I just need a little help
understanding, sweetie, okay?
Can you tell me where you came from?
- Where you've been all this time?
- [TV PLAYING INDISTINCTLY]
A policeman and a woman came
looking for you last year.
Did they find you?
She won't get better...
will she?
They don't think so, no.
[SNIFFLES] But she's not in any pain.
She's just stuck, they think.
Like in a dream.
A long dream.
A good dream?
I hope so.
[ELEVEN SIGHS]
Is it the same dream?
[BECKY] We don't know.
Sometimes she says different words.
But usually those.
[CRIES SOFTLY]
She always believed that
you were out there.
you'd come home one day.
Home?
Yeah, home.
[ELEVEN SNIFFLES]
[DOOR CREAKING]
Pretty.
I can get you a real bed, and
you can stay here with me
if you want.
How's that sound?
I wanna help you, but...
to really do that, I need
you to talk to me, okay?
Doesn't have to be now.
Doesn't have to be today.
But when you're ready.
Okay?
Okay.
[BECKY] Oh, yeah, that.
That happens sometimes.
Old house, bad wiring...
Or if you ask my crazy
aunt Shirley, it's...
haunted.
Sweetie, really, it's just the wiring.
No.
[MUTTERING INDISTINCTLY]
It's Mama.
Sunflower. Rainbow.
Three to the right. Four to the left.
[STUTTERS] I don't understand.
Four-fifty.
She knows I'm here.
[TV CHANNELS CHANGING]
She wants to talk.
Rainbow.
- [STATIC HISSING]
- [TERRY SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[BOB] All right.
All right. I'm 3.6
inches, what do you got?
I'm not sure. Mrs. Byers?
Hold on.
Twenty-one feet, four inches.
What about Tippecanoe to Danford Creek?
[SIGHS AND STAMMERS] Danford?
Where's Danford?
Dining room.
[SIGHS] Sixteen feet, ten inches.
What about Danford to Jordan?
Oh, come on. [STUTTERING]
This has gotta be enough.
It's not. It's... it's really not.
Okay. Can't you figure it out?
[STUTTERING] Well, it's hard.
The ratio isn't exactly one-to-one.
I mean, if you're twisting my arm,
and you are twisting my arm,
I would say that the X is...
maybe a half mile southeast of Danford?
[SIGHS] Thank you. Thank you.
What? Are we... we really going?
[KAREN] I don't know, Cath.
Maybe if it was Margaret Thatcher,
that'd be another story.
[DOORBELL RINGING]
Just a second, Cath.
Ted, can you get that please?
Sorry.
I got it.
Your line has been busy for
over two hours, Mr. Wheeler.
- Do you realize this?
- Oh, I do realize.
- Is Mike home?
- No.
No? Well, where the hell is he?
Karen, where's our son?
Will's!
- Will's.
- [SIGHS] No one's picking up there.
Nancy. What about Nancy?
Karen, where's Nancy?
- [SIGHS] Ally's!
- Ally's.
Our children don't live here anymore.
You didn't know that?
- Seriously?
- Am I done here?
Son of a bitch. You're really
no help at all, you know that?
[TED] Hey! Language.
Listen...
I've been thinking...
I love you. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry? What the hell am I sorry for?
Steve.
Are those for Mr. or Mrs. Wheeler?
- No.
- Good.
- Hey. What the hell? Hey!
- Nancy isn't home.
- Where is she?
- Doesn't matter.
We have bigger problems
than your love life.
Do you still have that bat?
- Bat? What bat?
- The one with the nails?
- Why?
- I'll explain it on the way.
- Now?
- Now!
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
[GROANING]
[COUGHING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GROANS]
Son of a bitch!
[GRUNTING]
[YELLING]
Wait. Wait. No, no! No! No!
[GRUNTING]
[YELLING]
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
[LUCAS] And that was the
last we ever saw of her.
After that, she was just gone.
I can't believe it's been that long.
Feels like yesterday.
Yeah. I mean, I bet.
- Wow.
- It's crazy.
[SIGHS] I know.
It's crazy, but...
I really liked it.
- Liked it?
- Yeah.
- Well, I mean, I had a few issues.
- Issues?
I felt it was a little
derivative in parts.
What are you talking about?
I just wish it had a
little more originality.
- That's all.
- You don't believe me?
Lucas, come on, seriously? How
gullible do you think I am?
Why would I make this up?
I don't know. To impress
me or something?
Or you're just, like, insane.
I tell you all of this. I
mean, top-secret stuff.
Risking my life. And
this is how you react?
[CHUCKLES] Risking your life?
- Oh, so this is funny to you?
- Yeah. I mean...
kind of funny.
Stupid, but funny.
Where are you going?
Story time's over, isn't it?
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
What's wrong with you? I
gave you what you wanted.
I wanted to be a part of the
group, not a part of some joke.
It's not a joke.
You did a good job, okay?
You can go tell the others
I believed your lies
if it gets you experience
points or whatever.
[SIGHS]
We have a lot of rules in our party,
but the most important
is, "Friends don't lie."
Never ever. No matter what.
Is that right?
Then how do you explain this?
[SIGHS] I had to do that.
To protect you.
To protect me from who, exactly?
The big bad government
baddies from Hawkins Lab?
Lower your voice.
Maybe it was to protect me from the
Demogorgon from another dimension?
- Max, I'm serious, shut up!
- Oh, no, no!
You know what it was? It was Eleven.
The girl...
Stop talking.
You're going to get us killed.
Do you understand?
You're serious?
I really wish I wasn't.
Prove it.
I can't.
So what? I'm supposed to just trust you?
Yes.
- [CAR ENGINE REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
Shit. I gotta go. Um...
Don't follow me out. Okay?
Do you believe me?
[ROCK SONG PLAYING ON STEREO]
The hell I tell you?
I'm not late.
You know what I'm talking about.
- Oh, Lucas?
- [SCOFFS]
- So he has a name now, huh?
- [STAMMERS]
It's a small town, okay?
We weren't hanging out.
Hmm. Well, you know what
happens when you lie.
I'm not lying.
[OWENS ON TAPE] What if
they try to replicate that?
The more attention we
bring to ourselves,
the more people like the
Hollands who know the truth,
the more likely that scenario becomes.
You see why I have to stop the
truth from spreading, too.
Just the same as those weeds there.
By whatever means necessary.
[TAPE RECORDER CLICKS]
So, is it enough?
The tape recording, is it enough?
[STUTTERS] Is it incriminating?
[LIQUID POURING]
- What are you doing?
- Thinking.
With vodka?
It's a central nervous
system depressant.
So yes, with vodka.
[NANCY] Music? Really?
Yes. It helps me...
- [JONATHAN] What? Think?
- [SIGHS HEAVILY]
[JAZZ SONG PLAYING]
How long is this gonna take?
Longer if you keep talking.
Is the tape incriminating or not?
It's a simple question.
[LAUGHS]
There's nothing simple about it.
Nothing simple about
anything you've told me.
You don't believe us, do you?
I believe you, but
that's not the problem.
You don't need me to believe you.
You need them to believe you.
- Them?
- Them.
With a capital "T."
Your priest, your postman, your teacher,
the world at large. [SCOFFS]
They won't believe any of this.
That's why we made the tape.
Oh. That's easy to bury. Easy.
He admits it. You heard it.
He admits culpability.
You're being naive, Nancy!
Those people...
[CHUCKLES]
They're not wired like me and you, okay?
They don't spend their lives
trying to get a look at
what's behind the curtain.
[CHUCKLES] They like the curtain.
It provides them stability,
comfort, definition.
This...
this would open the curtain,
and open the curtain
behind that curtain, okay?
So the minute someone with an ounce
of authority calls bullshit,
everyone will nod their heads and say,
"See? Ha! I knew it! It was bullshit."
That is, if you even get
their attention at all.
You're saying we did all
of this for nothing?
I'm saying, I'm thinking.
Ooh!
[GRUNTS]
[JONATHAN] This is ridiculous.
- That's it. That's it!
- What's it?
It's just too strong. Too strong.
Better.
Perfect.
We water it down.
- Precisely.
- Wait. What?
Your story. We moderate it.
Just like this drink here.
We make it more tolerable.
Perhaps Barbara was exposed
to some dangerous toxins.
A leak from the lab. Like Three
Mile Island or something.
Something scary but familiar.
Close enough that it hits the
man right where it hurts.
And those assholes that killed Barb...
They'll go down.
[TAKES DEEP BREATH]
[OWENS] All right, what
are we looking at?
[LAB TECHNICIAN] This was some
of the soil we took yesterday.
Okay. So what is your concern?
Well, we didn't find any
signs of contamination.
Uh, nothing hazardous other
than some pesticides.
Well, it's a farm.
Right, right. Exactly. But...
Like this?
Yes.
[STATIC HISSING]
It's okay if I sit here, right?
Yes.
[STAMMERS] And I won't
mess it up or anything?
- No.
- Okay.
If you talk to Terry, will you tell her
that I love her very much?
And that I'm sorry that
I didn't believe...
- Stop talking.
- Okay, sorry.
Breathe. Sunflower. Rainbow.
Three to the right. Four to the left.
Four-fifty.
Breathe.
Breathe. Sunflower. Rainbow.
Three to the right. Four to the left.
Four-fifty.
- Breathe.
- Mama?
- Sunflower. Rainbow.
- Mama, it's me...
Three to the right. Four to the left.
- Four-fifty.
- Jane.
Breathe. Sunflower.
I'm here now.
Four-fifty.
Breathe. Sunflower. Rainbow.
I'm home.
No.
[ECHOING] Mama!
[TERRY SOBBING]
[PANTING AND GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
- Mama! Mama!
- [SOBBING]
- Oh, my baby!
- What do I do?
- Mama, what do I do? Help me!
- [BECKY] Breathe. Breathe.
Just breathe. Breathe.
Just breathe, all right?
They're on their way.
- They're on their way, okay?
- Okay.
[GASPING]
Stay with us, darling. Stay with us.
[GROANING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[VENTILATOR HISSING]
- [BABY CRYING]
- [GRUNTS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[MONITOR BEEPING]
Hey, there.
[SIGHS]
Jane?
- Where's Jane?
- I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
No, I saw her.
- No, no, she wasn't breathing.
- She was crying.
- No.
- I heard it. He was there.
- Who was there?
- He took her.
[BECKY] Don't take it out! Terry!
- Terry!
- [TERRY] No! No!
- Please don't!
- [NURSE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[TERRY] Three to the right.
Four to the left.
[LOCK CLICKING]
[SIGHS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Ma'am, can I see your badge?
Stay back. Stay back!
- [GUNSHOT]
- [PEOPLE SCREAM]
[ALARM BLARING]
Jane? Jane?
Jane... No!
No! No! She's my child! No!
She's my child!
No! No.
No.
[GRUNTING]
[SOBBING] No. No. No.
Ah!
Four-fifty.
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
[GASPING]
Breathe. They're on their way.
[NURSE] Stay with us, darling.
- [BABY CRYING]
- [TERRY] Sunflower.
Three to the right. Four to the left.
- Rainbow. Four-fifty.
- Breathe.
- [BABY CRYING]
- [TERRY] Sunflower. Rainbow.
Jane... No!
- Four-fifty.
- Breathe.
- Three to the right. Four to the left.
- [BECKY] Breathe.
- [TERRY] Sunflower. Rainbow.
- Three to the right. Four to the left.
- [BECKY] Breathe.
[TERRY] Four-fifty. Sunflower. Rainbow.
[GASPING]
Sunflower. Rainbow. Three to the right.
Four to the left.
Four-fifty. Breathe. Sunflower.
There's nothing. There's nothing here.
- Are... Are we close?
- We're in the vicinity.
What's that mean, the vicinity?
It means we're close. I don't know.
It's not precise.
But we did all that work.
[BOB] I told you, the scale
ratio is not exactly
one-to-one. We needed to take...
- Turn right.
- What?
- I saw him.
- Where?
Not here. In my now-memories.
- [BOB] In your what?
- Turn right!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[ALL SCREAMING]
Are you okay?
Superspy.
What's Jim doing here? Joyce?
Boys, I need you to stay here.
No. Mom, Mom, Mom, it's not safe.
That's why I need you to stay here!
Stay here!
Hopper!
- Hey, be careful.
- [PANTING]
Just going down the hole.
Vines.
Give me that.
- The shovel?
- Yes, give me the shovel.
[JOYCE GASPS]
[SCREECHING]
[SIGHS] I need you to
help me get down there.
- Joyce, what are you talking about?
- Bob! Now!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Hopper!
- Hopper!
- [BOB GRUNTS]
Joyce, what is going on?
- Where are we?
- [STAMMERS] Bob, are you okay?
- [PANTING]
- Tunnels. Is this Will's map?
Hopper!
Are we in Will's map?
Hopper! Hopper!
[BOB] We're in Will's map.
[JOYCE] Hopper!
[BOB] We're actually
inside of Will's map.
[JOYCE] Hopper!
[BOB] How did he know all this?
[JOYCE] Bob!
Over here!
[STAMMERS] It's his.
[SIGHS] He's gotta be this way.
Come on. [GRUNTS]
Hopper!
Do you see anything? I mean,
in your now-memories?
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[JOYCE] Hopper!
Hopper!
What?
This is...
Oh! It's his arm.
[JOYCE GRUNTING]
[BOB] It's choking him.
Knife.
- [JOYCE] Knife?
- It's over there.
[JOYCE] Okay.
[ALL GRUNTING]
Hands!
[COUGHS AND GRUNTS]
Cut it...
[SCREAMS]
[SCREECHES]
Bastard!
[SCREAMS]
[JOYCE PANTING] Oh, my God.
Hopper, are you okay?
- Joyce.
- Are you okay? Are you okay?
- Hey, Bob.
- Hey, Jim.
- [SCREECHES]
- [JOYCE] Oh, God!
[JOYCE SCREAMS]
Go! Go! Go! Clear the area!
- Go!
- [HOPPER] Wait.
[MAN] Move, now!
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[SCREECHING]
[WILL GRUNTING]
[MIKE] Will? Will, you okay?
- Will, what's wrong?
- [GRUNTING]
[SCREECHING]
[WILL SCREAMING]
synced & corrected by PopcornAWH
www.addic7ed.com
[SYNTHWAVE MUSIC PLAYING]