Previously on Riverdale...
Bee and Vee, ladies...
You're not allowed to go around
humiliating girls for any reason...
If you wanna ride the Chuck
wagon, that can be arranged.
If you hadn't come when you did...
Where is he?
The Pussycats already saved me.
Am I supposed to pay you?
I do you a favor.
One day, you do me a favor.
You went to see Penny Peabody?
Do not contact her again.
If she reaches out, don't respond.
[JUGHEAD] The cops are
rounding up Ghoulies!
[TALL BOY] You called the cops?
You think I knew Keller
was gonna be there?
- I called Keller.
- What the hell, Archie?
I found out who killed Jason Blossom.
I found out who the Sugarman was.
You're next.
- [GUNSHOT]
- Black Hood.
[STATIC]
[NARRATOR READING] _
_
"People of Riverdale,
I have rid this town of the
drug-dealing child-killer
and others like him."
"Now, you must choose your fate.
The next 48 hours will be a test.
And I will be watching
you very closely."
"Show me you are pure of heart,
and my work ends.
Continue to sin,
and I will take up the sword again."
I thought I'd finally
outsmarted him, Jug,
the Black Hood...
By having Mr. Phillips arrested,
I thought I was saving
his life, but instead...
Hey, Betty,
Phillips didn't deserve what
happened to him, but he was...
A high school teacher dealing drugs.
- I mean, Betty if it...
- And how the hell
did the Black Hood even get
into the Sheriff's Station?
I mean, unless he...
What?
What is it, Poirot?
Nothing. No. It's too crazy.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hello.
It's Penny Peabody,
remember that favor you owe me?
I'm calling it in.
Uh, no, no. Wait,
wait, hold on a minute.
I'm hungry, I'll meet you at Pop's.
[LINE DISCONNECTS]
[SCOFFS]
I can't do this favor
for you, whatever it is.
If I have to pay for
you helping my dad...
He needs more help, that's why I called.
FP got in a little "accident",
with some Ghoulies in the
prison showers the other day.
Oh, my God.
Listen. He's in the infirmary now.
Is he okay?
Well, they messed up
that pretty face of his.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
The Ghoulies wanted blood payback
for the deal you and
that Northsider made
with Sheriff Keller, got all
their higher-ups locked away.
That wasn't...
What can we do, to get him out?
For that you would need
money. You need money.
Rich people?
Rich people don't sit in jail.
Money greases the wheels of justice.
I have $18 to my name.
Hmm.
Well, then maybe we should
think of this favor as a job.
Right?
Just a one-time delivery.
You just pick up a
crate on the Southside,
deliver it to an address
in Greendale. That's it.
What's in the crate?
Let's say, um...
Pancake mix.
Penny, I'm not gonna
be your drug-runner.
Of course not. You're gonna be
my "transportation advisor."
Do this,
and I'll use your cut of
the cash for your dad's case.
I'll see what we can do about
getting him an early release.
Okay. Okay, I'll do it.
Good boy. Okay. Now, you
just gotta make the drop off
and get out of there before midnight.
'Cause you don't want to be in
Greendale after midnight, trust me.
All right? And, um, this crate,
it's not gonna fit on your bike.
Can you get a car?
_
Jug? What are you doing here?
Out of the way, Bert & Ernie.
Archie, listen. I need your help.
You owe me,
because of that little stunt you pulled
with Keller and the Ghoulies.
Whatever you want.
Name the time and place, and I'm there.
It's tonight. And we need
to borrow your dad's truck.
Archie... No questions asked, okay?
[SLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Grab that side of the
crate, I'll grab the other.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Jug, I will see this through,
but where does it end?
115 Derby Street in Greendale.
Come on. I mean, how does
you being a Serpent end?
I don't know.
[SIGHS]
I'm kind of just living
minute-to-minute here.
All right?
You know, I had this stupid idea.
That after graduation,
instead of going to college,
we'd both move to New York.
You were this writer.
And I'd be this musician,
we'd both live in, like, the
East Village or something.
Just doing our thing.
Pretty sure the East Village
doesn't exist anymore.
Where are Betty and
Veronica in this scenario?
They're roommates on Park Avenue.
No, but seriously,
you stay on this path, Jughead,
you're gonna end up in jail.
Or maybe worse than jail.
[TIRES BLOW, SKID]
And of course, I don't
have a friggin' spare.
We're gonna have to call Triple C.
What? We have the crate in the back.
No, no. Let's call Betty.
She can bring us a tire.
Are you crazy? No,
Betty is not an option.
I am not letting you
drag her into this mess.
Hey, calm down. You're right.
Kevin! He's got a truck.
Let's call him. Come on.
Yeah.
[SIGHS]
[LINE RINGING]
[TRUCK HONKING]
Okay.
Play it cool.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Having some car trouble?
- No.
- [JUGHEAD] Yeah.
We need a spare.
Or a ride to Greendale, if you can help.
Uh, no spare,
but I'm passing through Greendale.
What's in the crate?
Pancake mix.
Well, I can take you, but
it's going to cost you.
- How much cash you got?
- $18.
I only got room for one of you.
Me. And the crate.
You're not seriously gonna
go with this guy alone, are you?
We don't really have any other choices.
[MCGINTY] Hey, we doing this or not?
[JUGHEAD] Yeah, yes we are.
It's all right. Just stay
with your dad's truck.
Hey, you've come this far.
We're all good.
Okay?
[MCGINTY] Don't look
under that tarp, boy.
[ENGINE STARTS]
Thought your friend back there was
Jason Blossom,
for just a hot minute.
You never know on the road to Greendale.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
This is truly judgment day,
and he is the reaper,
for Riverdale is soulless and corrupt.
But in the Black of the
Hood is the light of God,
and when you see it, you will die.
Unless you are of heavenly
things and pure...
Do you mind if I turn this down?
There's a lot of righteous people
saying he's doing God's work,
The Black Hood.
That's one way of lookin' at it, yeah.
Yeah.
You know what this
whole Black Hood thing
reminds me of, don't you?
The Riverdale Reaper, is what.
Riverdale had a Reaper?
Makes my blood run cold
just thinking about it.
- [ARCHIE] Thanks for the tire.
- [MAN] You got it.
[MCGINTY] Fill her up.
I'll go pay inside.
[CAR DOOR SHUTS]
[FAINT BUZZING]
[FLIES BUZZING]
[BUZZING CONTINUES]
[MCGINTY] Hey, boy!
There's a cafe over there.
I'm starving. Come on, now.
[LIVELY MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO]
I saw you, look under my tarp.
Don't worry, I got my permits.
I'm no thrill-seeking sicko,
like the Black Hood.
Or the Riverdale Reaper.
Who exactly was the Riverdale Reaper?
There was a family living
out near Fox Forest.
[BOTTLE SQUIRTS]
Good family.
Mother, father, two kids.
One night, they were all asleep,
someone broke in.
A boogeyman went room
to room with a shotgun.
Shot 'em all dead.
No survivors.
Oh, my God.
Did they find him? The Reaper?
Some people say the lynch mob got him.
Hung him from the
tree near Pickens Park.
Others think he hopped a train
and went out to California.
Started praying to the Devil.
Others say he never left Riverdale.
What are you saying?
You think the Riverdale
Reaper is the Black Hood?
I'm saying that there's
a cycle to things.
What happened then,
what's happening now.
It's killing season in Riverdale.
And I wouldn't be surprised
if it was the same man.
[TEARS PAPER]
Here's the check,
when you're ready.
My friend here'll pay for it.
What?
[NERVOUSLY] I don't have any money,
I gave it to you... 18 bucks.
I used that for the gas.
Well, somebody's gotta pay for this.
Oh, good luck, Crown
Boy. I'm outta here.
And I'm taking that crate with me.
- No, you aren't, man.
- [WAITRESS] Hey! Where are you going?
Nobody move, I'm calling the Sheriff...
- No!
Jughead, what's going on?
They're trying to dine n' ditch!
I'm calling the cops!
Two boys on a country road,
with a crate full of God-knows-what.
You're sinners, both of you.
Careful or you'll taste
the Reaper's blade next.
I'll pay for the bill.
Do you take debit?
Hey.
Thanks.
And thank you for coming back for me.
I said I'd see this through, Jug.
[SIGHS]
It's 11:52.
Better get goin' then.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[WHEELS SQUEAKING]
You're late.
We had car trouble.
- [STAMMERS] Whoa, whoa.
- Next time don't be late.
No next time.
No, this was a one-time thing.
That's not what Snake Charmer tells me.
She says the Serpents are
taking over for the Ghoulies.
We're set for a regular delivery,
with a regular delivery boy.
Which one of you is Jughead Jones?
You know my name?
Ah.
["JUST ME AND YOU" PLAYING]
[ENGINE STARTS]
♪ When I think of you ♪
♪ My heart remembers ♪
[TIRES SCREECHING]
♪ All the love we never had ♪
Thank you for helping me tonight, I...
I know that, that
violates every strand of your DNA.
We've all done bad things, Jug.
Ever since the Black Hood
walked into this diner.
It's like he's making us do them.
I was thinking about that guy
who stopped for us tonight,
Mr. American Gothic.
His story about the Riverdale Reaper.
Maybe it's just a tale
from the dark side but...
What if,
it's an actual lead?
Maybe tomorrow,
you and I,
if you're free, we
could go to library...
Me and Reggie are taking
Moose to physical therapy.
Then Ronnie and I are having dinner
with her parents.
But maybe the day after?
Yeah. For sure.
Can't you get out of this somehow, Jug?
What part exactly?
I can try.
Hey, I'll try.
[SIGHS]
Do you want a ride home?
It's practically dawn.
No, um...
Visiting hours start at sun up.
I'm gonna visit my dad.
[PHONE RINGING]
[RINGING CONTINUES FAINTLY]
[DOOR BUZZES]
What's up? You look
like you've seen a ghost.
[JUGHEAD] What the hell game
are you playing, Penny?
- You lied to me. My dad's fine.
- I incentivized you.
No, you said that this was
gonna be a one-and-done.
It's not like you have a choice.
What is this?
It's insurance you'll do what I say.
And if you cause a stink
or try to back out,
or raise your voice to me ever again,
I will make sure that video goes
straight to the Sheriff's office.
God, imagine what that
would do to your dad's heart.
Break it, right?
[PENNY SIGHS]
Why?
- Why me?
- FP made me a promise,
that he didn't keep.
As far as I'm concerned,
his debt is yours.
And I am just getting started with you.
[DOOR CLOSES]
_
[VOCALIZING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[GASPS] Mr. Svenson,
you scared me.
I was about to lock up.
Are you gonna be okay?
Yeah, yeah, I'll just, uh,
slip out the side door, like usual.
As long as you don't
tell Principal Weatherbee.
He'd have my head.
[EXHALES]
[CONTINUES PLAYING]
♪ Everything ♪
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Josephine McCoy.
[SIGHS]
Why do you think I moved
us into the Five Seasons?
Because,
you don't feel safe at the house.
Baby, I don't want you
walking the streets alone,
not with the Black Hood out there.
I am this close to assigning
a deputy to you for security.
Mom! I don't need a bodyguard.
I'm not Whitney.
[SNAPS FINGERS] Not yet, anyway.
I want you in this hotel
before dark from now on.
- [SIGHS HEAVILY] Mom.
- Understood?
Yes, ma'am.
The Black Hood has my mom on
edge and she has me on edge,
and when I get stressed,
the polyps on my vocal chords swell
and I lose my voice.
On top of which,
going behind the Pussycats' back,
working on songs without them.
You feel like you're sinning, and
the Black Hood is going after sinners.
I get it. And you're
allowed to feel guilty.
Up to a point,
but I slipped that vid of
you singing "Milkshake"
to that producer at
Shabbey Road Studios,
and he was adamant about
giving you and you alone,
- studio time.
- [CHUCKLES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
OMG. Another gift from
your secret admirer?
Gotta get a new lock.
That's the third gift this week.
Who could this mystery bae be?
[GASPS] Ooh, maybe it's the Black Hood.
You know he loves writing notes.
That is not funny, Cheryl.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
["SPOOKY" PLAYING]
♪ I get confused ♪
♪ I never know where you stand ♪
♪ And then you smile... ♪
[KNOCK AT DOOR]
Chuck Clayton? Can I help you?
Well, I heard that voice
and I could not resist.
So, uh,
I know this may seem a
little out of the blue.
But I was wondering
if maybe you and I...
No.
Not even some cheese fries at Pop's?
Wait, hold up.
Are you the one putting
things in my locker?
- Well, I can be.
- Ew.
Sorry, Chuck. I don't date.
Especially not chauvinistic,
misogynistic harassers of women, like you.
[SIGHS]
- [SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
- I've got bio.
You will not believe this.
Chuck Clayton just
asked me out on a date.
That's vile, assuming you said no.
Yeah, I'm not insane.
Good. Because we've a date
with the recording studio
- [SIGHS]
- Maybe after school today?
No way. I'm heading straight
to the girls' locker room
for a eucalyptus steam.
My throat's been acting up...
- Josie, we have to practice...
- Good Lord, Cheryl.
I don't know who's more
controlling, you or my mom.
Josie, what you did,
saving me from that Nick St. Creature.
It's a debt I'll never be able to repay.
What I can do is offer my humble
skills to make your career blossom.
But I'm happy to take a step back
if you're feeling overwhelmed.
No, no.
It's all good.
[EXHALES]
Oh, my God...
Hey, what's up.
Is it true you're ditching us?
- Who told you that?
- Someone put a note in my locker.
- What?
- Josie.
Women are supposed to treat
each other better than this.
We're your sisters, and
you clawed us in the back.
It's not as black-and-white as that.
Okay, this... This opportunity
just fell in my lap.
[VALERIE] Then why
didn't you talk to us?
Why be all shady and hide it?
Because she wants to
try it as a solo diva.
Well, go ahead, Josie.
Try it, girl. 'Cause
you're on your own now.
What? No, wait! No, Val!
Pride cometh before the fall, Josie.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Who's there?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMS]
God! Chuck!
Chuck!
- [PANTING] Oh, my God.
- Josie, are you okay?
Yeah. [CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
I'm fine.
[NERVOUSLY] Hey, you wanna...
You wanna give me a ride home?
Yeah, yeah, of course.
[WHISPERS] Okay.
Is it cool if we make one stop first?
Don't.
Don't give me that look.
That "we are on a date" look.
We are not on a date.
Okay, I admit,
- I don't have a great track record.
- Hmm.
But I am changing.
I started going to church with my dad,
and I'm taking these art classes.
Why? To objectify models?
No, I wanna draw comics
or kids books.
Chuck, be realistic.
You expect me to just
believe that you've changed?
[POP] Hey, kids.
Really nice seeing you at
church on Sunday, Chuck.
Maybe you can get this one to come.
What?
Did you plan that?
No, I'm good.
- But I'm not that good.
- [CHUCKLES]
And, Josie, I really
am trying to be better.
Come on, let's dance.
- In Pop's?
- Why not?
["SWEET LITTLE SIXTEEN" PLAYING]
♪ She gets so excited ♪
♪ Watch her look at her run ♪
♪ Oh, Mommy, Mommy ♪
♪ Please may I go ♪
♪ It's such a sight to see ♪
[JOSIE GIGGLES]
♪ Somebody steal the show ♪
♪ Oh, Daddy, Daddy ♪
♪ I beg of you ♪
♪ Whisper to mommy ♪
♪ It's all right with you ♪
♪ 'Cause they'll be rockin on bandstand ♪
♪ In Philadelphia P.A. ♪
[MAYOR MCCOY] Josie!
- You are a damned fool.
- Mom, what are you doing here?
Check your phone, young lady.
I've been texting you for hours.
And you're in here doing the twist.
Mom, relax.
[NERVOUSLY] Mayor McCoy, I was just
about to give Josie a ride home.
You?
I don't want you within
ten feet of my daughter!
I cannot have you acting out, Josie,
not with everything that's going on.
I'm not acting out, Mom,
I'm living my life.
There are people in this town
with hate in their hearts.
You've read the letters I used to get.
The words they used.
And now, since the Black Hood started,
it's gotten so much worse.
It's like...
It's like they're emboldened by him.
I've started getting death threats.
Oh, my God.
The things they're saying, Josie,
they're going to "slit my throat."
Or "cut out my heart."
They're monsters.
And...
What?
The last letter I got,
mentioned you.
I have to ask you, Josie,
you received any letters? Or packages?
Anything suspicious or threatening?
No.
No, nothing like that.
I've worked so hard to get us here.
To shield us from this kind of hatred.
Mom.
[SOBBING]
[CHERYL] That someone would do that,
write those things to your mom?
This town is seriously ill.
Tell me about it.
My mom's the mayor.
She's the strongest woman I know,
and for these cowards
to be terrorizing her...
Do you want to bail on practice?
No, I need to sing.
It'll keep my mind off last night.
Speaking of,
I cannot believe you went on
a date with Chuck last night.
Taking a few art classes
does not a saint make.
He really is trying
to be a better person.
Is that why you didn't
tell Sheriff Keller
he was low-key stalking you?
I'm giving Chuck the
benefit of the doubt.
Fine. It's your funeral.
Here we go again.
I'll give Chuck that.
He knows how to commit.
[CHERYL] Oh, my God.
That is so not okay.
It's a threat, Josie.
What's in the box?
[GASPS] Oh, my God!
Out of the way, Bert and Ernie.
We got your note, Cretin.
This sick game you're
playing with my girl ends now.
Some people may be buying
the snake oil you're
peddling, but not me.
You're still the same
Chuck that thinks women
are playthings to possess and torture.
Cheryl, what are you even
talking about right now?
Stuffed animals are one thing,
- but a pig's heart?
- Josie, I, uh...
If the Black Hood weren't
clearly an old white dude,
I'd say you'd be a prime suspect.
Hey, what's going on here?
Oh, good. Mr. Svenson's
here to clean up the trash.
Chuck's been threatening Josie,
sending her disturbing messages.
The creep probably wants to
cut her open and feel her organs.
Josie, is this true?
For all we know, he's the one
sending your mom those letters, too.
[CHUCK] Come on, Josie.
It is. He's the one.
- What?
- It's true.
It is not true, and you know it.
- You're going to Weatherbee's office.
- You are lying!
- You're lying! You're lying!
- Come on!
[CHUCK] All right!
[STUDENTS CHATTERING]
We spoke with Chuck and he'll be
steering clear of you from here on out.
I'm glad they found the miscreant
that was doing this to you, baby.
Actually, we may not have.
We spoke with Chuck and questioned
him and checked his locker,
but we never found any evidence.
Well, keep looking, Tom.
If my daughter says it's him, it's him.
["SPOOKY" PLAYING]
♪ Just like a ghost ♪
♪ You've been a haunt in my dreams ♪
♪ But now I know ♪
♪ You're not what you seem ♪
♪ Love is kinda crazy with a spooky... ♪
♪ ...little boy like you ♪
♪ Spooky ♪
[SLASHING]
[CHOKING]
- [SHRIEKS]
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
[PANTING]
Josie, baby, what's wrong?
[MUTED GROANS]
Baby, what's wrong? Say something!
Say something, Josie.
["SPOOKY" PLAYING]
[JOSIE SINGING]
♪ You call me up and ask me ♪
♪ Would I like to go with
you and see a movie? ♪
♪ Mmm ♪
♪ First I say no, I've got
some plans for tonight ♪
♪ And then I stop ♪
What is it, Poirot?
Nothing. No. It's too crazy.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
There's no way.
[KEVIN] You guys, I'm worried about my dad.
The town is turning on him.
He's trying his best under
these crazy circumstances,
but this Black Hood stuff
is really getting to him.
- How is he dealing with it?
- Yeah, what's he been doing?
He's not sleeping.
He's not eating.
I hear him rummaging around the house
at odd hours, talking to himself,
just heading out in
the middle of the night.
- Where do you think he's going?
- Where's he going?
I don't know. But
whatever it is, it's...
It's like he's a different person.
Poor Kevin. He's like a character
in a lost Tennessee Williams play.
Veronica, I have a theory
about Sheriff Keller.
Oh, me, too. It's obvious.
- He's the Black Hood.
- He's having an affair.
What?
Is that a joke?
I wish it were.
Whatever crazy web that
you're spinning, Bee,
let me break it down for you.
Sheriff Keller's wife's away,
he's failing at his job,
he's looking for comfort,
sneaking around...
All signs point to cheating.
Well, I don't know, maybe
he's having an affair,
and he's the Black Hood.
You've known Kevin's dad how many years?
Okay, think about it,
The Black Hood killed Mr. Phillips
in a cell at the Sheriff's Station.
How do you explain that?
Betty, Kevin needs our
friendship right now,
not your groundless suspicions.
[EXHALES] Don't worry,
my intuition's telling me
that he's having an affair.
But stay tuned while I prove it.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
So I've been wracking my brain for
something that might cheer you up,
and I have just the prescription.
A sleepover!
- Doesn't that sound fun?
- A sleepover at the Pembrooke?
Actually, Kev, I was thinking how
I've never seen your house.
Thank you for sitting
down with me, Sheriff.
Like I said, I'm writing a
follow-up about Mr. Phillips.
Well, I'm happy to oblige, Betty.
How did the Black Hood get
to the Sugarman, Sheriff?
Right here in the station?
Forced entry. I was out on patrol
and the overnight
deputy, he fell asleep.
But breaking into your
station, that seems...
Incredibly ballsy?
Have a look at this.
The Black Hood pried the
door open from the outside.
An then he just... Well,
come on, I'll show you.
[GRUNTS]
I'll take you down to the holding cells,
where he shot Phillips.
We've gathered shoeprints,
video surveillance and
everything else we could
to catch this monster.
But what enrages me is that
it happened in my department,
under my watch.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
And if you roll a six,
you can take over the
Kingdom of Theodore.
[VERONICA] Interesting.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Uh...
I'm gonna go get a bevvy.
Do you want anything?
A glass of milk would be great.
- Betty?
- You're having a sleepover at Kevin's?
Without me? In the middle
of an investigation?
This isn't an investigation, okay?
This is me helping a friend deal
with his father's infidelities.
Oh, so you're there snooping to prove
that Sheriff Keller's having an affair?
Why else would I leave the
comforts of the Pembrooke?
Can you please add looking for evidence
that suggests Sheriff
Keller's the Black Hood
to your to-do list?
I'd start in the home office.
It's locked.
And, no, I don't have any bobby pins.
Okay, check the basement.
Yeah, I'm sure that's where
he keeps all his spare hoods.
[DOOR CREAKS]
No way. I am not going down there.
Please. Just check to see if
something jumps out at you.
[SIGHS] Okay, fine.
[FLOOR CREAKS]
[MAN GRUNTING]
[LOUD GRUNTING]
[BETTY] Hey, Vee...
[PANTING] Oh, Veronica.
What can I do for you?
[STAMMERS] I was just...
Looking for juice or
diet soda or something.
The fridge in the kitchen is empty and
I'm parched.
Well, there's some here, I think.
- There you are.
- [SIGHS] Thanks.
[PANTS]
I didn't know you worked
out so much, Mr. Keller.
[GIGGLES] I mean, Archie
Andrews, watch your back.
[SCOFFS] I don't do it for vanity.
I do it for discipline,
and to push my limits.
- And I'm sure it comes in handy on the job.
- Yeah.
Kevin mentioned things
have been stressful lately,
with the Black Hood and everything.
It must get super hard.
With all the pressure,
without Mrs. Keller.
Where is she stationed, again?
Bahrain. Uh, some Naval Base there.
That can't be easy.
How do you...
Cope?
[KEVIN] Veronica?
What are you doing down here?
Hey, pal.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
[VERONICA ] I saw Kevin's dad sneaking
out in the middle of the night,
and he came home, like, at 4:00 a.m.
Look.
A Jingle-Jangle addict's body was
found by the tracks this morning.
It says here this guy was
hit and killed by a train.
Yeah, because he was
pushed in front of it
by Sheriff Keller.
Or he stumbled into its path.
No, think about all the locked
doors in his house... Why?
- Why?
- Because he's a private person.
Look, Betty, let's not confuse
wanting a solution to this mystery
with actually having one, okay?
This is Kevin's father
we're talking about.
[SIGHS]
["SPOOKY" PLAYING]
♪ You always keep me guessing ♪
♪ And I never seem to know
what you are thinking ♪
[ENGINE STARTS]
♪ And if a fellow looks at you ♪
♪ It's for sure your little
eye will be a-winkin' ♪
♪ I get confused 'cause I
don't know where I stand ♪
♪ And then you smile ♪
♪ And hold my hand ♪
♪ Love is kinda crazy withьa
spooky little girl like you ♪
♪ Spooky, yeah ♪
[DOORKNOB RATTLING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUNSHOT]
[SHERIFF KELLER] Betty?
What are you doing here?
[HAL] Thanks for calling, Tom.
That's okay, Hal.
And as for Betty, I... I apologize.
[STAMMERS] I mean, accusing
you of being the Black Hood.
I can't imagine where she got that idea.
Well, she found my research
on the case, and, uh,
the black hood that I pulled
out of Archie's locker.
With an overactive imagination,
I can see how it could
look a certain way.
This is my log book.
Go ahead and flip through it.
When Fred was shot, I
was processing a perp.
When Midge and Moose were
attacked, I was patrolling downtown.
And I was right here in the station when
Ms. Grundy was murdered in Greendale.
Graveyard shift.
Betty, I'm not going to say anything
to Kevin about what happened.
You've been a very good friend to him.
I think this would break his heart.
[HAL] Thanks, Tom.
I know you think I'm crazy, Vee,
but you yourself, saw him sneaking out.
- He's hiding something.
- Okay, Bee.
I'm in, for Kevin's sake.
And also to keep you in check.
Look. Look, look, look!
[ENGINE STARTS]
Where-oh-where do you
think you're going, Sheriff?
[ENGINE STARTS]
- There he is.
- [VERONICA] What is he doing?
[BETTY] That must be his kill kit.
His what now?
He's about to do something terrible.
His next victim could be
in that room right now.
Should we call the cops?
Betty?
[WHISPERS] Betty!
[KNOCKING]
- [WHISPERS] What the hell are you doing?
- Shh.
[BETTY] I just can't
believe this. I'm in shock.
Me, too.
My woman's intuition told me
Sheriff Keller was having an affair,
but with Mayor McCoy?
Oh, God. Riverdale's list
of sinners keeps expanding.
Hey, look, it's the boys.
Shall we ask them to join?
On second thought, it looks like
they're having an intense broment.
Veronica, how are we gonna
tell Kevin about this?
I don't think we do.
I think this is one of
those secrets we keep.
For Kevin's sake.
Let him keep thinking
his dad's a good guy.
There, there.
Drink your tea, Josie.
Do you want a ride home?
It's practically dawn.
No, uh,
visiting hours start at sunup.
I'm gonna visit my dad.
[PHONE RINGING]
[RINGING CONTINUES]
Hello. Pop's!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
That was him on the phone.
The Black Hood.
He says that we've failed his test.
That we're all sinners.
That the reckoning is upon us.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --