[Jughead] Previously on Riverdale...
[gun fires]
[Pop] This man... His
goal was something else.
It was like Angel of Death
had come to Riverdale.
[screaming]
Hello, Dilton.
Somebody has to teach them how to stand
their ground. The way this town is going...
[Ms. Weiss] Your father's
facing serious jail time.
[Tall Boy] Serpents
take care of their own.
We got your back.
Smithers, would you describe
my father as a good man?
I'd rather not say, miss.
I told your father that you were...
Conflicted about helping him.
"If you do not testify, your poor mother
might be drawn into this awful mess."
Whether or not Sheriff Keller finds
the person who did this or not,
you don't have to worry.
I'm gonna protect you.
I swear it.
[Jughead] Behold, Pop's
Chock'lit Shoppe.
For decades, the
heart of Riverdale.
What the hell?
Now, the latest casualty in
the town's ongoing battle
against darkness.
[bell jingling]
-Pop?
-[Pop] Did you see?
Did you see what they wrote
on my Chock'lit Shoppe?
[Archie] No, no, no, no.
[Fred coughing] Do we
need a fire extinguisher?
What are you doing up? I was
going to bring you breakfast.
I appreciate it, son.
But I've gotta get to
moving around sometime.
Little early for that, isn't it?
No, I'm good.
Dad, the only thing you
need to be worrying about
is getting better.
[phone ringing]
Crap. I gotta take this.
I gotta go. Bye.
Hi. Sheriff Keller?
No, no. Deputy, I've been leaving
messages for the sheriff.
I need him to call me
back about my dad's case.
[sighing]
TTFN, Smithers.
Oh, wait, Ms. Veronica. You might
want to take the side exit.
-Why?
-[door opening and closing]
[Hiram] Yeah, why, Smithers?
Because she might bump into me
coming in from an early run?
[Veronica] Good morning, Father.
Mija. You leave
before breakfast,
you come after your mother
and I have had dinner.
I can't remember the last time
we had meal together
as a family.
I can. It was at the Dakota.
The day you got arrested.
Well, perhaps we should
talk about that.
Tonight, at dinner.
The three of us.
Unfortunately, I have plans.
To quote that  New
Yorker cartoon,
how about never, Dad,
is never good for you?
[Jughead] It's another
win for the bad guys.
No one was there. His
entire staff quit.
He says he's not sure how long
he'll be able to
keep the doors open,
maybe not even a week.
It's because of what
happened to my dad.
People are freaking out. And
I gotta be honest, guys,
I don't see myself going
back any time soon.
Wait, I'm sorry, am I
hearing acceptance?
I'm not letting one
psychopath with a gun
dictate what happens
to our place.
Jug, you went crazy trying
to save the drive-in.
I can't take on any more
social issues right now.
My hands are full.
With your dad, of course.
And he should be your priority.
[sighs]
I'll take point on
helping Pop Tate.
I'll help, too, Betty.
Hey, anything to get me away
from my parents, I'm in.
Another Bee and Vee team-up.
They should really make a
video game about you guys.
-[giggles]
-[Jughead] I gotta jet.
I'm off to meet my dad's
court-appointed joke
of a lawyer at the
sheriff's station.
I'm gonna come with you, Jug.
I gotta drop some flyers
off for Sheriff Keller.
[Veronica] Bye.
[door opens]
Sheriff Keller.
Archie, how's your
dad holding up?
Honestly, he'd be
doing a lot better
if you caught the
guy who shot him.
We're doing everything we can.
Yeah, me, too. I'm out
here handing out flyers,
talking to neighbors,
tracking my dad's credit cards
because his wallet
is still missing.
Which means this guy has all
of our personal information,
including where we live.
And we were witnesses.
If your guys are out there
patrolling, Sheriff,
-let me go with them, I can help.
-Oh, no.
[man over police radio]  10-4.
We've got a 53 in Greendale.
Greendale? All right, copy that.
Just give me a sec.
Let us do our job.
You take care.
Let's talk about the damn deal.
First, to review the
charges you're facing,
arson, destruction of evidence,
making a false confession,
obstructing justice,
not to mention this
whole nasty mess of dumping
a dead kid in the river.
I know what I did.
What's the deal?
What are they offering?
You're gonna want to take it.
I'm telling you, I've been
doing this a long time.
It's a strong deal.
How many damn years?
[creaking]
Whoa, whoa!
-Jughead. Are you insane?
-Hey
You're the one that looks like a Dream
Warrior from Nightmare on Elm Street 3.
What did the lawyer say?
I've been walking around all night trying
to wrap my head around how bad it is.
It's bad.
My dad is facing 20 years, Arch.
Crap, Jughead, I'm sorry.
That sucks.
The lawyer thinks he
should take the deal.
And that if he doesn't, and the case goes
to trial, he could be facing 40 years.
I'm just really, really scared.
Yeah, me, too.
About what?
[gunshot sound]
I couldn't sleep
last night, Jug.
I kept thinking about
your dad, and Pop's.
And how maybe we can kill
two birds with one stone.
Can you meet me at
the Mayor's office?
Okay, great, I'll get it set.
But right now, I need to call...
Hey, Bee, what's up?
[knocking at door]
I know you haven't been
sleeping in your room.
So where exactly have you
been spending your nights?
[Archie] So, Betty.
[Veronica] Yes, Betty.
Ever since you and your dad
got home from the hospital,
she's noticed your room's been
unusually empty and quiet.
Why?
So I can... Watch the doors.
So I can make sure
no one comes in.
I know it sounds crazy, but
the guy who shot my dad
is still out there, Ronnie,
and I'm scared he's
gonna come back
and finish the job.
Archie,
you went through something
deeply traumatic.
Can I make a suggestion?
Please. Anything.
When I lived in New York,
I saw a therapist once a
week to help me get through
all sorts of Park Avenue drama.
Now, I'm not saying to go
see a therapist, Archie,
but maybe the school
counselor could help?
[Betty] Mayor McCoy.
Betty, Jughead. What
can I help you with?
So, the Chock'lit Shoppe is
on the verge of closing,
and we want Pop Tate to
know that the entire town
is rallying behind him.
We were thinking
that you could...
[stammering] Make the
building a landmark,
or declare a "Pop's
Day" in support?
What if I endorse Pop's, and next
week someone else is shot there?
My priority as a mayor and as a
mother is keeping this town safe.
If we have to close
Pop's, I'm all for it.
Are you also "all for" shipping
my dad off to a state prison
-for a murder that he didn't commit?
-Shh.
What is this, an ambush?
I know you have an in
with the State Attorney.
If you could just call him and try
to get my dad a better lawyer,
anything?
Your father made some mistakes,
I'm sure he'll get
a fair hearing.
[Jughead] Mayor McCoy?
You remember this moment.
'Cause this is the moment
that you turned your back
on both Pop Tate and my father.
Midge Klump.
The Klumpster.
Reggie,
what do you know
about jingle-jangle?
I know you shouldn't say it so loud
while we're on school property.
[whispering] And that
I can score you some.
Who's it for?
Me and Moose.
Lemme see what I can do.
What's on your mind, Andrews?
Girl troubles, scabies?
Why are you seeking guidance from Ms.
Burble?
-I'm not.
-Maybe you should.
You look like my nuts
after football practice.
Hey. Do you have anything
that can help keep me awake?
Many things.
Amphetamines, Baclofen,
Modafinil, jingle-jangle.
Jingle-jangle?
That'll keep you up for days,
in more ways than one.
But why do you need
uppers, Wonder Bread?
Until the guy who shot
my dad is caught,
I wanna be on high alert.
So, can you help
me or not, Reggie?
I got you, Andrews.
[slap]
[Betty] We can't let
the terrorists win.
We need to host
an event at Pop's
that reminds the town
of simpler times.
Like, a throwback to when the
shoppe first opened its doors.
Betty, I like a good milkshake
as much as any girl,
and Pop's puts Serendipity
3's to shame.
But, why this hill to die on?
Orange freezes with my mom
and Polly after ballet.
Chicken noodle soup with my
dad after ice-skating...
Grilled cheeses with Archie on
the last day of summer vacation.
It's where I met you for
the first time, Vee.
It's where I met you
for the first time.
Also...
Jug.
He may lose his dad,
but maybe I can save this one
place for him... For all of us.
[knocking at door]
Hey. Veronica. May
I speak to you?
Daddy?
-Daddy?
Every day I was in prison, I
thought about getting back to you
and your mother.
And I knew it wouldn't be easy,
I knew it would take time.
Meet me halfway.
Don't you think I
want to, Daddy?
Don't you think I want everything
to go back to the way it was?
The three of us, walking into
some fabulous gala or ball.
You with your two
favorite girls.
But...
I can't.
The blindfold's off, Daddy, I
can't just put it back on.
I'm sorry, but I should
get back to my friends.
Yeah, hey, so... Were you, uh...
Planning a dance in there?
An event. To keep
Pop's from closing.
Well, if I can help in any way--
I'll let you know.
[Jughead] I tried going
the legit route.
I even talked to the mayor.
It's just...
It feels like the whole
system's rigged against us.
What's FP saying?
Is he taking this deal?
Not if I can help it.
Tall Boy...
What if we bust him out of jail
before he gets
transferred to state?
[Tall Boy scoffs]
It's totally doable.
The sheriff's station
has worse security
than Riverdale High.
And once he's out, it's just a straight
shot right up Sweetwater River
until the Canadian border.
You've seen  Escape From Alcatraz
a few too many times, kid.
Your dad needs a snake-handler.
Someone whose livelihood
depends on snakes.
Who's used to dealing with 'em.
I got someone you should meet.
[Cheryl] Humpty and Dumpty.
Just in time to meet
our newest recruit.
In addition to my
duties as a Pussycat.
And, I just wanna say,
girls, I'm so excited
to work on my moves
and to be a team player,
as long as I'm in the front.
Wait, Cheryl,
does that mean you're taking
the Vixens back from me?
But, really, Veronica,
were they ever yours?
Cheryl, we were wondering if
maybe the Vixens would help
at an event to save Pop's.
Oh, Betty.
I did not emerge from the frozen
depths of Sweetwater River,
nor the flames of Thornhill,
to allow my Vixens
to sling milkshakes
at some death-cursed diner.
The answer is a
double-cherry-on-top no.
Okay.
Great talk.
[Weatherbee] May I have
everyone's attention?
I have some tragic
news to share.
Ms. Grundy,
who was a teacher
here last semester,
was found
murdered in her Greendale
home last night.
Oh, my God.
[Weatherbee] I know some of
you were students of hers,
and that this news will
be difficult to process.
[inaudible]
Mr. Andrews?
First, you get shot.
Then, Ms. Grundy is murdered.
All within a matter of days.
Dad, what if some crazy person is going
after the people that I care about?
What? You think I'm nuts?
No, son, I think you're scared.
Understandably so.
Truth is, son, we don't know anything
about what happened to Ms. Grundy.
She's dead, she was killed.
Right across Sweetwater River.
I know.
It was a horrible thing.
Don't you wanna find
out who did this?
Who's doing this?
-[tattoo needle buzzing]
-[rock music playing]
I'm, uh, here for Penny Peabody?
[Penny] Forgive
the office space,
but I'm a firm believer
in low overhead.
Plus, I like being
close to my clients.
Your clients...
Being the Serpents?
Well, I was and
still am a Serpent.
They put me through college,
law school.
Right.
The Serpents are often on the
other side of the law, so...
Having one of their own,
on retainer, helping out
is clever.
Well, FP always bragged
that you were smart.
Oh, yeah, I know your dad.
And I also know, from
our, uh, mutual friends,
the deal he's been offered.
It's garbage.
Can you help?
I know the loopholes. In
this case, there are none.
But, if you get the victim's
family to forgive him,
in front of a judge,
that might shift
things in FP's favor.
Instead of 20 years, he
can get time served,
-with parole.
-Oh, that's great.
Yeah.
Thank you. Uh, am I
supposed to pay you, or...
We're friends.
I do you a favor.
One day, maybe, you
do me a favor.
Let me know how it
goes, will you?
Tell your dad to wear a tie.
You're twitching, Archie. Which
means this must be serious.
I think the same
person who shot my dad
may have murdered Ms. Grundy.
My, my.
We've come a long way
since dances at the gym
and varsity football
tryouts, haven't we?
[sighs] You were the first to know
anything about Jason's autopsy, Mom.
So, Archie's wondering if...
If I can get details on Ms.
Grundy's death
and see if they line up
with the attack on Fred.
It would be really helpful to
put Archie's mind at ease.
Fine. I'll reach out
to my ghoulish friend.
-Thank you, Mrs. Cooper.
-Mm.
-Thanks, Betty.
I should go.
I'll call you, Arch.
Spreading ourself a little thin
as the patron saint of lost
causes, aren't we, Betty?
Oh, you can cross saving
Pop's off your list.
Oh, haven't you heard?
Pop Tate is selling
the Chock'lit Shoppe.
What? To who?
To, and you'll love this,
an anonymous buyer.
Ring any bells?
Oh, Ms. Veronica. I'll
take those for you.
-Oh, thank you, Smithers.
-[phone ringing]
Hey, girl.
What?
Are you buying Pop's?
The way you bought the drive-in?
Anonymously?
And are you doing
this just to buy me?
Yesterday, at school,
did you think,
"Oh, Veronica's working so hard
to save the Chock'lit Shoppe,
I'll just save it for her!"
Veronica, I'm not buying Pop's.
Now, please, lower
your voice and sit
so we can speak civilly.
Do you really want to talk, Dad?
That's all I've wanted.
A fair hearing.
To explain myself.
Okay.
Let's talk about Mr. Andrews.
Mom asked him to sell his
portion of the SoDale project,
and the day after he
rejected the offer,
he was shot in Pop's.
Was it your doing?
Veronica, first you accuse
me, then your father?
No, no.
I didn't shoot Fred.
Nor did I hire someone to do it.
I was your fiercest
protector, Dad.
Ask Mom.
Whenever somebody called
you the devil incarnate,
I defended you.
I kept telling myself,
"He's not that bad.
You can forgive him."
And then you sent me this.
A letter threatening you, Mom.
That's the kind of man you're
letting back into our lives.
[Hermione] Veronica?
Your father didn't
write this letter.
I did.
I don't understand.
I needed you to testify
on your father's behalf.
So I wrote this letter.
Threatening myself.
Not your father.
She did it for us.
To survive.
So we can be a family again.
You two deserve each other.
It's not exactly
downsizing, is it?
[knocking at door]
Hobo. Bride of Hobo.
Welcome to Thistlehouse.
Mother's in the conservatory.
Follow me.
Thank you for sitting
down with us.
Of course, Betty. You're family.
[Jughead] Okay.
The reason we're here...
FP's lawyer thinks that if
the family of the victim
shows mercy...
Mercy.
That's why you're here?
Well, it's an appeal
for leniency from you.
To reduce my dad's sentence.
Where was your father's mercy when
I spent those countless nights
walking the halls of
Thornhill in agony,
obsessing over what was
happening to Jay-Jay?
Imagining the worst.
Where was your father's mercy
when I slept under the same
roof as a cold-blooded killer,
night after night.
Cheryl...
FP didn't kill Jason.
Okay? That was your dad.
You saw the video.
If it were up to
me, I'd watch FP
fry in the electric chair.
We need this sordid
chapter closed forever,
and FP is the last
loose end to tie up.
I will not have a living,
breathing reminder
of the darkest
chapter of my life
walking the streets
of Riverdale.
What do we do now that
Cheryl's gone full Poison Ivy?
Blackmail. Extortion.
If they weren't weren't literally an
orphan and a widow, I would do it.
[sighs]
[coroner] Lacerations on the neck.
Her trachea's crushed.
Broken veins in her eyes
and the skin tears
suggest brutality.
This is a crime of passion.
Hatred.
He wanted to feel her
struggle as she died.
Tell me, Mrs. Cooper, did
you know the victim?
No.
[grunting]
Stop!
It's me.
Are you freakin' insane?
What the hell are you
doing here, Reggie?
Delivering your uppers, clearly
the last thing you need.
You've lost it, Andrews.
You're the one here
wearing this hood.
It's called a prank,
I didn't expect
you to attack me.
What if I had been the guy? Eh?
You would have just tackled him?
Yeah. Damn right.
He has a gun, Andrews.
He's shot people.
Only a dumbass lunatic brings
a baseball bat to a gunfight.
[both panting]
There was no sign
of forced entry,
which probably means
she knew her killer.
The police don't know if any of her
personal belongings were taken.
How, uh...
How did Ms. Grundy die?
The autopsy showed that
she was strangled.
With something the
killer grabbed on hand.
A cello bow, of all things.
There was a struggle.
She fought back.
But, Archie, this was
a crime of passion,
in another town with a completely
different murder weapon.
The likelihood of these two
crimes being connected
seems slim.
Son...
If I say what I'm thinking, you're
just gonna think I'm crazy.
Probably Mrs. Cooper's right.
Probably they're not connected.
[Jughead] So, why'd
you do it, Pop?
Did they make you an offer
you couldn't refuse?
Who's buying it?
Do you even know?
[Pop] It shames me to say.
ChugMo.
The liquor store chain?
Hey, could I make a request of you, Pop?
For a last supper?
Anything you want.
Actually, it's not for
me, it's for my dad.
He's facing 20 years
of that weird meatloaf
that they serve prisoners.
So, barring an eleventh-hour
miracle, I was
kind of hoping for his
last meal in Riverdale
that you could make
him his favorite.
Fried chicken,
cornbread, onion rings
and an orange freeze,
if memory serves.
It's very Rain Man of you, Pop.
Been doing this a long time.
Thought I'd be doing it
until the day I die.
This is...
Unacceptable.
-What?
-Just everything.
Pop, have you officially
sold the diner?
The contract's being drawn up.
Do not sign it.
Okay? Do not give up.
Either of you.
I can fix this, all right?
I will fix this.
Okay? Bye.
-[door closes]
-[gasps]
Give a girl a warning, will you?
You want closure, Cheryl.
I want to help my
boyfriend's dad.
I already told you.
And I'm telling you
to help FP.
-Or...
-Or what?
Or I wide-release the video of
your father shooting Jason.
Try having closure with
that out in the world.
I thought you gave that damned
thumb drive to Sheriff Keller.
No. Not before I saved a
copy onto Jughead's laptop.
One click,
and the darkest chapter of your
family's twisted psychodrama
becomes a viral sensation.
Are you threatening me?
This? No.
No, this is...
Fun girl talk.
You could save a man's life.
Think about that.
A nice ending to a sad story.
If I testify,
you're giving me that video.
And a guarantee that any
and all other copies
in your possession
will be erased.
You have my word.
Also,
I need the Vixens.
For Retro Night.
You're a stone-cold
bitch, Betty Cooper.
I don't have red hair,
nor broad shoulders,
or a blonde ponytail,
for that matter.
Do you wanna talk?
You were ready to walk away
from your dad.
And now, you're crusading
for his freedom.
What changed?
He did.
He made an effort.
Took another swing
at being a good dad.
But don't you think
some people can't change?
Like, it's just in
their DNA to be bad?
I'm not gonna presume to know
what lies in your father's heart.
But Archie's dad almost died.
And my dad is going
away for 20 years.
If there's even a .0001% chance
-that your dad is trying--
-I get it.
Thank you, Jughead.
Sheriff, I believe the
man who shot my dad
is the same person that killed Ms.
Grundy.
And I think I know who it is.
You know, that's, uh... That's
quite a statement, Archie.
Ms. Grundy had an
abusive ex-husband.
She moved to Riverdale
to get away from him.
She kept a gun in her car in
case he'd ever come back.
How do you know all this?
Because she and I were...
We were close.
And I'm thinking... He
found out about me.
Ms. Grundy was killed
with a cello bow.
I gave her one before
she left Riverdale.
I'm betting it's
the murder weapon.
Can't you see, he's
sending me a message.
Your theory's wrong, Archie.
My counterparts in Greendale
already brought in her ex.
And he has an airtight alibi.
[exhales]
Maybe everyone's right.
Maybe I am going crazy.
Hey, has Betty called?
Not yet. Let's pray Cheryl
comes through for them.
[judge] Ms. Blossom, you may
proceed with your statement.
Your Honor, I speak for myself
and my mother when I say
we forgive FP Jones for
the part he played
in covering up my
brother's murder,
and we humbly ask the
court for leniency.
FP's guilt has been
blown out of proportion
to satiate what my father's
suicide denied us.
Closure.
As much as I sympathize,
I can't ignore the quality of Mr.
Jones' crimes.
There were no extenuating
circumstances.
My father threatened him.
I overheard them talking
in Daddy's study.
Daddy said he would hurt
Jughead if FP didn't comply.
Is that extenuating enough?
[judge] In light of
these revelations,
I suggest that we
take a step back
and reevaluate certain
aspects of the case.
At which time, we will
revisit the sentencing.
Adjourned.
Is that a win?
It's a delay. So, yeah.
[sobbing quietly]
No one's here.
No one's coming.
It's still early, okay?
Mom.
What, did you come to gloat?
Oh, don't be so
cynical, Elizabeth.
I came to write my next story
over one last root beer float.
I'm calling it
"Requiem for Pop's."
Can I get a quote, dear?
You're a fiend, Mother,
but this is one obituary
that you're not gonna write.
All right, two strawberries,
one vanilla,
and one chocolate
with extra malt.
[clears throat]
Why the hell did you broadcast
all over social media that
the Pussycats would be doing
a free concert here tonight?
I knew that if I asked
you, you would have said--
-No!
-Mmm-hmm.
If my mom even hears that I
set foot in this place--
Josie, you care about this
place, I know you do.
I see you in here all the time.
Betty, even if I wanted
to help, I'm down a cat.
-Valerie has norovirus--
-I don't mind stepping in.
After all, if you can
be a River Vixen,
Josie, I can be a Pussycat.
As long as it's a cover, I'm
sure I'll know the lyrics.
I mean, you do love your
cheese fries, Josie...
[sighing]
Fine. Fine.
[Josie singing]  ♪ My milkshake
brings All the boys to the yard ♪
♪ And they're like It's
better than yours ♪
♪ Damn right It's
♪ I can teach you But
I have to charge ♪
♪ My milkshake brings All
the boys to the yard ♪
♪ And they're like It's
better than yours ♪
♪ Damn right It's
♪ I can teach you But
I have to charge ♪
♪ I know you want it ♪
♪ The thing that
makes me Oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ What the guys go crazy for ♪
♪ They lose their minds ♪
♪ The way I wind I
think it's time ♪
[Veronica] Hey there, Daddy-O.
-Hey.
-You made it.
You feeling okay?
Yeah. Just taking deep breaths.
I'm proud of you.
Come on, you take a booth.
And I'll get you a shake.
We're not here to fight,
we're here to be supportive.
Dad, Mom.
I've been thinking.
Tonight is a new beginning for Pop's.
And...
Maybe it can be for us, too.
That's up to you, mija.
If that's what you want.
Let's try. But, you guys,
total transparency, okay?
From now on.
In the spirit of
that, I propose that
Lodge Industries make a
charitable contribution.
[camera shutter clicking]
Relax, Betty.
I'm sure they're
just here to enjoy
Pop's world-class
burgers and service.
Just like me.
[Cheryl] Ugh, you two are
like chimps in captivity,
grooming and picking
lice off each other.
Mark this day in your diary.
I lied under oath for you. And
thank God I'm quick on my feet.
Cheryl,
thank you.
Honor your promise to me.
[sighs]
Boo!
Hi, Midge, Moose.
I've got your jingle-jangle.
[camera shutter clicks]
[Pop] I gotta put
her on the spot.
It's thanks to this
young lady here
that Pop's gets to stay
open tonight, tomorrow...
As long as you
folks keep coming.
[crowd cheers and applauds]
Thanks, also, to
the Lodge family
for a donation they just made
that gives us a little cushion
to weather any storm
that might come up.
I didn't know we were in
the charity business.
Oh, we're not.
As of five minutes ago,
we, uh, own this diner.
In exchange for silence, I told
Tate he could stay on as manager.
-Nice to have you back, Hiram.
-[chuckles]
Hermione, thank you for
saying you wrote that letter.
Veronica never would have
forgiven me for that.
Once again, your loyalty
knows no bounds.
Ronnie, should I introduce
myself to your dad?
You've faced enough
dragons for one night.
Next time, Archiekins.
So, I guess tonight is a
win for the good guys.
A rare win, but, yes.
Thanks to you, Betty.
You okay?
I'm here with you guys.
So, yeah. I think so.
[Cheryl] I have a
present for you.
The video of Daddy and Jason.
All cued up.
It might bring you peace.
[man] Evening, Mr.
and Mrs. Lodge.
You must be Veronica.
I am. Where's Smithers?
Oh, he didn't tell you?
His mother fell ill so he went
home overseas to care for her.
Did he leave a
forwarding address?
I'll try to track one down, sir.
Thank you, Andre.
[cell phone ringing]
Hello?
You went to see Penny Peabody?
You asked her for help?
Dad, hey...
Yeah, well, we didn't have a choice.
Why, is something wrong?
Did you pay her?
No, she said it was a favor.
[FP] Jughead, listen to me.
Do not contact her again.
If she reaches out,
don't respond.
You do not want to be in bed
with the Snake Charmer.
Why? Dad--
You do know that several drug
deals went down here tonight.
What?
And if you think
that Hiram Lodge,
Riverdale's answer to Scarface,
helped Pop Tate for
altruistic reasons,
I have a bridge to sell you.
Mom...
The Serpents have now
officially crossed the tracks
and have a toehold
on the north side.
So, congratulations, Betty.
You're almost
single-handedly responsible
for giving crime a
haven in Riverdale.
[bell jingling]
[Jughead]  And far from the
glow of Pop's neon sign,
on Sweetwater Bridge,
Archie Andrews had arranged
a secret rendezvous
with Dilton Doiley.
Hey, Dilton.
Hey, Archie.
Got what you asked for.
I'm not crazy.
The guy's still out there.
It's just for protection.
Sure, Archie. Whatever you say.
[Jughead] That night, for
the first time in weeks,
Archie would sleep.
Before waking up the next
morning to a living nightmare.
[Midge] Bottoms up.
[giggles]
Oh, wait, wait.
I think there's
somebody out there.
No, don't. He'll see us.
[gunshots]