Previously on Riverdale...
He calls himself the Black Hood.
It's like the angel of
death had come to Riverdale.
A family of four was murdered.
There was a third child.
Do you know who killed your family?
A preacher, passing through town.
A group of men killed him.
Justice had been served.
I know all about the Snake Charmer.
If you cross the stink,
I will make sure that video goes
straight to the Sheriff's office.
I love you, Ronnie.
Archie, whatever
deep-seated issues I have,
I can't let myself go there with you.
How many times are we
gonna push each other away?
Used to be, in ye olden days,
every December, a Lord of Misrule
presided over the winter holidays,
called back then, the Feast of Fools.
What do you say, Pop? Is it okay?
The best tree yet.
Thanks, Archie, thanks, Fred.
Oh, no. Thank you, Pop,
for letting us set up shop
right in front of your diner.
You guys gonna stay in town for break?
Yeah. We were gonna visit my mom,
but she booked a single's cruise so...
How are you and Veronica?
We've been better.
If it's any consolation,
Betty and I aren't in the
greatest of places, either.
Jughead, you want a Christmas
tree, you and your dad?
On the house.
It'll have to be a small one, Mr. A.
So, I'll see you at
Kevin's Secret Santa thing?
Yeah. Because that
sounds like a great idea.
So Christmas was happening,
even though this year's Lord of Misrule
was none other than the Black Hood.
Betty.
- Wake up, it's time.
- Polly.
- He's here, he's waiting for us.
- What? Who?
You know who. Come on.
Merry Christmas.
Hey, Merry Christmas.
- Betty.
- Betty, Merry Christmas.
- Okay.
- All right, honey, I told you like...
Santa?
- Where's Jason's stocking?
- I couldn't find it.
And anyway, there's
nothing to put in it.
And what, pray tell, is this?
It's going to be a Hard Candy
Christmas this year, Cheryl.
Time to face facts. We have no money.
Dad, what is that? A
letter from the Black Hood?
No, it's worse.
Riverdale General. My hospital bill.
How much is it for?
- Eighty-six thousand.
- What, dollars?
That can't be right, can it?
Or doesn't your insurance...
They probably made a mistake.
I'll call them tomorrow.
Kevin's Secret Santa had
a strict $20 limit, V.
Kevin needs to relax.
Also, these aren't just
for Secret Santa, obvi.
I got an Hermes scarf for my mom,
a leather passport case for my
dad, now that he can travel again,
and a little something for my best girl.
And a bauble for Archie.
Because you're getting back together?
Because it was purchased pre-breakup.
And haven't you heard?
We're still friends.
Oh, yeah.
Isn't everyone?
I was thinking about our Penny problem.
My problem, not ours.
Well, I am the one she has
on camera delivering drugs.
How I deal with Peabody
is not your concern.
I'm handling it.
By pimping the Serpents
out as drug runners?
Boy!
Toss them in the corner.
Hey, what's in the bags, Tall Boy?
Hey, what did I just say?
Mind your damn business
and get to school.
Veronica, it's your turn.
Hmm.
Oh. A gift certificate
for a couples' massage.
Thanks, Josie.
You can go with Betty, or your mom...
Or I can go with your mom, if you want.
Oh, dear God, can we please
get this torture over with?
Betty, you're next and mercifully last.
Well, I think I know who picked my
name based on these wrapping skills.
Archie...
My dad and I were cleaning
out the garage and I found it.
Swiss Family Robinson?
Yeah, It's this old read-a-long record
we used to listen to
when we were, like, five.
Oh, my God.
I love it, Arch. Thank you.
Hey, Merry Christmas.
- Moose.
- Hi.
Why are you rushing off?
Look, Betty,
I don't wanna be that guy,
but I see Moose,
all I think about is the Black Hood
and the pain he's caused
to the people I care about,
including you.
I know.
And the fact that he's still out there
is giving me anxiety nightmares,
making me paranoid.
Like, everywhere I look, all I see is...
What?
All you see is what?
Excuse me. Who are you?
You mean, my name?
Uh, where's Mr. Svenson?
No idea. He's been out a few days,
they just called me in.
Arch, you and Veronica
confronted Mr. Svenson
about his connection to the Black Hood.
And now he's not here.
What if something happened to him?
Betty, we found out
Mr. Svenson's secret...
What if we led the
Black Hood right to him?
What if we got him killed?
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Mr. Svenson?
He's been out all week with a cold.
Sounded terrible on the phone.
So, I dropped off some chicken
soup at his house a few days back.
You saw him?
I left it at his door.
But between us,
he often gets this way
during the holidays.
You know, depressed.
No family.
Thank you.
Hey.
I... stayed behind
because Merry Christmas.
Thank you.
I'm kinda sorry
for how it all went down between us.
The Serpents, my dad and I
specifically are in a precarious place.
I...
I just don't want you
in those crosshairs.
That's not your decision
to make, Jughead.
Even if you think it's to
protect me, it's my choice,
what I risk and for whom.
I know.
I should go. Check on my dad.
Jug.
I got you something, too.
Archie.
I got you a little something.
Thanks.
- I didn't realize...
- Oh, no, no.
It's all good. Just open it.
- Ronnie, this is...
- Turn it over.
I got it before...
I don't want things to
be forced between us.
What?
No. Did I... Did I make it worse?
I just, I wanted you to know
that I still care about...
No, you didn't.
Things at home aren't great right now.
It's my dad.
Anything I can do to help?
Come on.
We're still friends.
He just, he got his
hospital bill and he owes
$86,000, Ronnie,
and it's like we are
selling Christmas trees,
just for extra money so we
can keep our heads above water.
Oh, my God, Archie.
I want to help.
- I want to hug you.
- That's okay.
I shouldn't have said anything.
The watch is great, Ronnie. Thank you.
Yeah.
What is all this?
It's a Serpent tradition.
Every year, we give
back to the Southside.
Toys for Tots. Meals on Wheels,
kids and old folks living alone.
The Hells Angels do it.
I'm always down for charitable works.
Hey, have you seen my dad?
Why aren't you in school?
It's a half-day before break.
Well, in that case, you can
hold down the fort here, Jug.
Or I could come with you guys.
Nice try. The answer's no.
We do need another set of hands, boss.
There you go.
Let me pull my weight.
Dad...
I don't know what the Snake
Charmer has you doing...
Sweet Pea, you're with us.
Hey, Betty, what's up?
Hey, I can't let this Svenson thing go.
I think we should stop by
his house and check up on him.
Yeah, I agree.
Let me just tell my dad and we'll go.
- Give me ten.
- All right.
Teen Paul Bunyan, I'd like
to purchase your finest tree.
Actually, Cheryl, I was
just about to take a break,
but Vic here can help you. Vic.
What can I get you, miss?
We've got some nice spruces.
Well, there's the chicken soup.
Mr. Svenson?
Can I help you?
Jughead Jones?
Maybe.
I'm Jack Walsh, your
dad's parole officer.
He's not home.
Doesn't need to be.
Do you mind if I come in for a moment?
Like I have a choice.
Hiram. Was that a Spiffany's bag I saw
coming through the lobby earlier today?
It looked about the right
size for a Glamerge egg.
That depends, mi amore. Have
you been naughty or nice this year?
Don't worry, mi hija.
Santa has your list, too.
And please, don't go snooping for
the gifts this year. He hates that.
Santa can rip up my list for all I care.
I mean, look at us, throwing
money away on bejeweled eggs
like we're a family of Russian oligarchs
when there are people in this town
who can't even pay
their own medical bills.
And since when are you a communist?
Since Archie told me that he and his dad
are drowning in Fred's medical bills.
To the tune of $86,000.
Which is why I was thinking...
- Absolutely not.
- Sweetheart, that's a lot of money.
The Lodge Charitable Trust has made
its donations for the fiscal year.
Fred Andrews will have
to tighten his belt.
Said Ebenezer Scrooge.
Fred's selling Christmas
trees for extra cash, Dad.
I mean, that's the kind of
man, the kind of father he is.
You know,
I believe I've some work
to finish in my study.
Cheryl Marjorie Blossom,
what have you done?
Isn't it obvious, Mother?
I've saved Christmas.
Look how happy Nana Rose is.
You spoiled, wretched little brat,
how do you expect to pay for all this?
Oh.
I was thinking
maybe you could go to
Mr. Lodge for a job?
Of course, he'd probably
ask what skills you have,
and you'd be forced to admit
that the only skill you have
is being a terrible mother.
So, I guess you're going to have
to get creative in the New Year.
You should've drowned them at birth,
like a basket of kittens.
Mom?
Dad?
Hey.
How are you?
I'm fine. I just iced
some gingerbread cookies,
Polly's favorite, just in case
there's a Christmas
miracle and she comes home.
Oh, by the way, there was
a gift for you on the steps.
Your Secret Santa.
I took it up to your room.
Secret Santa?
"Enclosed is a finger that belongs
to the sinner Joseph Conway..."
He's talking about Mr. Svenson.
"You have one final trespass to unearth.
Find the truth, reveal it to the town,
and you will perhaps save his life."
He kidnapped Mr. Svenson, Arch,
and now he's mutilating him.
Arch, Arch. Hey.
Betty, please.
Mr. Svenson? Is that you?
It is, Betty, but his
name is Joseph Conway.
He's lost a lot of blood.
Though it's nothing compared to
the blood on the hands of this town.
Exhume the past.
Find where the primal sin was committed
and you'll find the
sinner Conway, maybe alive.
And, as always, don't...
What, you maniac? Don't
tell Sheriff Keller?
Archie, what sin?
What could Mr. Svenson
possibly be guilty of?
Veronica and I talked to him.
Betty, his entire family was
murdered by some crazy preacher.
Well, maybe the people who adopted
him know something that we don't.
Wait, wait, Betty.
Before he was adopted,
Mr. Svenson lived as Joseph Conway
at the Sisters of Quiet Mercy.
Would they talk to us?
They better.
Merry Christmas, Mom.
Pop's?
Did you open them?
No, Dad. Out of respect for you.
But your parole officer, Mr.
Walsh, he sure was curious.
- Walsh was here?
- Yeah.
Don't worry, I got rid of him.
But he already has heard that the
Serpents are moving
into narcos territory.
Ta-da.
Gift boxes.
- With drugs in them?
- No, with gifts in them.
For you, your mom, and Jellybean.
Christmas day, I thought
we'd take a ride to Toledo
and deliver them in person.
Dad, this isn't going to work.
Today, it's gifts.
Tomorrow, it's drugs or
weapons or God knows what.
And how long this is going to go on for?
As long as Penny wants.
And if her favors keep getting
bigger which you know that they will,
what happens when she asks
for more Serpents in on this?
Then I'll bring more Serpents!
You know what?
You are right. This isn't going to work.
You and I living together, so maybe
you can go back to Fred's or to Betty's.
Betty? I split with Betty...
Well then, what do you want me to say?
I just want you to let me help
fix this mess that I made.
Get this through your
thick skull, Jughead.
We are trapped.
We've got no leverage.
If that means I gotta be Penny's
dancing monkey for the time being,
then that's how it goes.
Let me get some rest.
I have a long night ahead of me.
Yes, hello.
I'm calling to settle an
account for one of your patients,
Fred Andrews.
Of course. I'm his business partner.
Uh-huh.
I'd like to pay the bill in
full and keep it anonymous,
an angel donation.
Yes, I'm aware of the amount.
My name?
Hermione Apollonia Lodge.
And it's a Black American Excess card.
Number 2-9-5-7-2-3-0...
Penny Peabody has got
my dad dealing drugs.
I know this,
'cause she had me doing it before him.
Now, she's roped in
Tall Boy and Sweet Pea.
Man, if you're pissed because your
old man tapped me instead of you...
No, Sweet Pea.
I'm pissed because I don't want the
Serpents to end up like the Ghoulies.
And I doubt that any
of you became Serpent
just to be at the beck and
call of a drug queen pin.
I know where this ends.
Death. Jail.
Which is why in the interest
of self-preservation,
we have to take out Penny.
Snake Charmer's helped some of us.
Oh, yeah?
And what did she ask for
in return, Sweet Pea, huh?
How many favors?
Now, if we don't stop Penny tonight,
she is going to get every single
one of us in on this. I promise you.
I promise you, Sweet Pea.
What I am asking is, are you
willing to risk your necks
to save my dad's life?
What is the first law?
No Serpent stands alone.
I'm in.
Me, too.
Let's do this.
Joseph Conway.
Joseph Svenson, as you know him,
was a troubled youth.
There was no saving him.
Meaning he was a sinner?
No, he was a child, a victim.
Did he suffer from survivor's guilt?
I've already said too much.
- No.
- Betty.
Sister Woodhouse,
when my sister escaped this dungeon,
she told me all about
the corporeal punishment.
So please, help us with this
or I'll expose the
Sisters of Quiet Mercy
for the house of horrors
that it really is.
After his family was massacred,
young Conway, young Svenson,
identified the man responsible.
Then, a small group
of Riverdale's citizens
took matters into their own hands
and, well, executed him.
It was only later when he was with us,
that Joseph admitted that
in his terror and shock,
he may have pointed a
finger of accusation...
At the wrong man?
Oh, my God.
Svenson's sin was sentencing
the wrong man to death.
Did Svenson, did Conway
ever talk about who
carried out the execution?
They came here once, to see Joseph.
It was a group of men and one woman.
I don't know their names
and I can't remember
what they look like.
Just that the woman had
the most striking hair,
white, save for a cherry-red stripe.
Nana Rose Blossom?
FP?
Well, you're early, Old Hoss.
Penny.
Ho-merry-ho.
Jughead Jones.
Nice crowbar.
This? Yeah, I brought it in case
I needed to pry the door open.
Well, are you gonna give
me hand with this stuff?
Your dad will be here in
like what, 15, 20 minutes.
He probably won't be too
happy to see you, huh?
I wouldn't worry about that.
Neither of us are going to be here.
Is this suppose to scare me?
I would not do this if I were you.
You are making a big mistake.
You are making a...
Hey, guys.
Finishing up some last minute shopping?
We were, but then we got the most
fascinating call from our bank,
confirming a charge that
was made to my credit card
in the amount of $86,000.
Oh, so that went through.
Great.
Yeah, I decided that you would
cover Fred's medical expenses.
I mean, if you can afford to buy Pop's,
and then lie to my face about it.
So, how is it that we can now
suddenly afford an entire diner?
You wanted a more active
role in Lodge Industries
and we let you have it.
Then you break into my office
and try to use whatever
you find as leverage?
Now, I admit, there's
a lot you don't know
and that's on purpose.
How can I be part of this family
if you keep hiding things from me?
Mija, you think you want to
know everything, but you don't.
My name is on all of those
documents in your desk, Daddy,
doesn't that mean I
have the right to know?
Yes. Yes, it does, Veronica.
But that means the time for
being Daddy's little girl is over.
It's time to work now,
all of us, in lockstep.
She deserves to know the truth, Hiram.
All right.
Follow me into the study.
Where am I?
You're in Greendale.
Your new home.
But frankly, Penny,
I don't care where you set up shop.
But it's not gonna be in Riverdale
and it's not going to be with Serpents.
You want to deal drugs,
you want to extort people,
that's your business.
But not on the Southside.
That belongs to us.
You stupid, cocky kid.
Serpent law says you
can't hurt one of your own.
Oh, Penny, it's time you learned.
Grab her.
What are you doing?
Get off of me.
Get off of me!
That tattoo doesn't make you a Serpent.
No!
Cheryl, we need to see your grandmother.
Nana Rose seldom has
visitors. She'll be pleased.
Entree.
Nana Rose, we have
some questions for you
about something that happened
in Riverdale a long time ago.
A man killed this family
and a group of people decided to
take justice into their own hands.
Oh, dear.
Here in Riverdale?
Yes.
And you were a part of
that group, weren't you?
What is this, a Christmas inquest?
Cheryl, a man's life is at stake.
Were you with this group when they...
When you killed this man for revenge?
Oh, no.
No girls allowed.
They told me to stay at home while
they took care of the bad man.
Nana Rose,
this is so important.
Where did they hang the bad man?
Oh, they didn't hang him.
Oh, no. They gave him a proper burial.
Buried him alive.
Where?
Where did they do that?
Ask your grandfather,
Polly dear, he was there.
My, my grandfather?
I had a picture of them,
smiling at the place.
Standing under the Devil's Hand.
Picture? What picture?
Cheryl.
I wonder if you might
take me to my room.
I suddenly feel quite ill.
Satisfied, you vultures?
Your reindeer games are over.
Now get the hell out.
Archie, my grandfather
helped murder an innocent man.
Betty, who even knows if
what she was saying is true.
That picture Nana Rose mentioned,
when Grandpa Louis died,
we packed up his house
and we donated most of his
stuff but he had pictures,
and we kept them and we organized them.
Okay, Betty, take a breath, where
are they? Where are the pictures?
My house. They are at my house.
- That's great.
- Archie,
my grandfather killed a man
in cold blood, an innocent man.
What if that's why he
picked me, the Black Hood?
That's why he has been calling me.
- Revenge for something I didn't even do...
- Betty, listen to me.
This is the part where we end this.
Where we save Mr. Svenson and
stop the Black Hood tonight.
But I need you with me.
I can't do this alone.
Tomorrow, we're gonna wake up,
and everything is gonna
go back to how it was,
but right now, I need you with me.
- I need Betty Cooper.
- Archie.
Betty.
We have to hurry.
Well, Veronica, now you know.
You know everyveing.
So, mija, what do you think?
I'm in.
But I have ground rules.
Well, one ground rule.
By all means.
I refuse to do anything illegal.
Well, that's fine,
especially since we're not
doing anything illegal either.
Let me share two words to live by.
"Plausible deniability."
Also,
that charge I made for
Fred's medical bills?
I want that to stick.
Mija, it's gonna complicate
matters, Fred's a proud man.
- He's not...
- We'll smooth that over, though.
And the truth is, we'll need
Fred for what comes next.
Fine.
Assuming the Fred
situation can be finessed,
do we have a deal?
We do, Daddykins.
We have a deal.
Hey, Dad.
What's all this?
This is a celebratory dinner.
Penny didn't show up for
your pick up, did she?
No.
No, she didn't. Why? Do you
know something about that?
She's gone, Dad.
I rallied the younger Serpents,
we drove her out of Riverdale.
And I got my pound of
flesh in the process.
Are you nuts? She will be
back, you better believe that.
She won't!
I was very persuasive.
And even if she does,
we will take care of it.
You and me, and the other Serpents.
- In unity, there's strength.
- Oh, God.
That's the sixth law.
While you were in jail,
I recited that every
day, I lived by that.
You want to take my jacket?
You want to relegate me
to Toys for Tots, fine.
But I am still a Serpent, Dad, and this,
this life that you
wanted to protect me from,
I'm proud of this.
I'm proud of who I am.
You can't take that away from me.
Nana Rose said it was a group of men.
I mean, there was one photo
that I kind of remember.
Dad said it was taken after Grandpa
Louis and some of his friends
had planted some trees in Pickens Park.
Wait.
Is this it?
Betty, look at the ground.
That's where they buried the preacher.
Where Svenson could
be maybe still alive.
Yeah, look at the branches.
The Devil's Hand.
That tree's in Pickens Park.
We'll call Sheriff Keller
on the way. Come on.
Look around. There.
Yeah.
Oh, my God! Archie.
Where is Mr. Svenson?
Why would the Black Hood
bury an empty coffin?
What if it's a...
Get in the coffin.
No. No way.
Get in the coffin or I
shoot her in the head.
Right now!
Shut the coffin and
step out of the grave.
Betty, do it.
I'm sorry.
Pick up the shovel.
Fill in the grave.
Please don't.
We know what Mr. Svenson's sin is.
What he did.
That's the town's secret sin.
That's what you want revealed, right?
We can do that. I can do that.
Mr. Svenson, wherever he
is, he doesn't have to die.
Archie doesn't have to...
Archie.
Where is he? Where did he go?
This way.
Hey!
Stop!
Right the hell now!
Get down or I'll shoot you.
I swear to God, I'll do it!
You tried to kill my
father and my friends.
You are going to pay for your crimes.
You are not escaping. This ends tonight.
I said stop!
Archie, put the gun down.
- It's okay.
- Sheriff Keller.
Stay back, Betty.
He's dead.
Who is he?
The town demanded blood for blood.
Give me the gun.
Your instinct about
Svenson was right, Ronnie.
You thought he was the Black Hood.
We could have ended it, right there
at school where we confronted him.
I didn't see it. I didn't,
I didn't see it in his eyes.
Forget his eyes.
I can't believe he
cut off his own finger.
The finger of accusation.
So we know whodunit.
Why did he do it?
Mr. Svenson accused an innocent man
of murdering his family
and got the man killed.
So maybe, in some backwards way,
he thought targeting sinners
would balance the scales somehow.
I don't know.
No, no, it makes sense.
I mean, Svenson was always
around, lurking in the hallways.
He could have seen me and
Ms. Grundy in the music room.
Yeah, he could have seen Moose
and Midge buying jingle-jangle.
Guys, this is starting to feel like
that weird last scene in Psycho.
The truth is...
I have nothing actually.
Except that he's in a
body bag and we aren't.
I think that's enough for tonight.
♪ God rest ye merry gentlemen ♪
♪ Let nothing you dismay ♪
♪ Remember Christ our Savior ♪
♪ Was born on Christmas Day ♪
Mother. Nana.
Is it time to open presents?
Santa?
♪ Oh, tidings of Comfort and joy ♪
Who's this one from?
Archie.
He dropped it off yesterday.
Let me guess that's from Betty.
Vintage Underwood.
It's the typewriter of champions.
You maybe, uh, want to swing by later?
Say thanks in person.
Oh, I'll just probably
call her or text her.
♪ Now to the Lord Sing praises ♪
♪ Of you within this place ♪
♪ And with true love
And brotherhood ♪
♪ Each other now embrace ♪
Wow, that sounds amazing, Mom.
Yeah, it's been, it's been quiet.
You, too. I love you, too, Mom.
All right, here's Dad.
Hey, there.
Merry Christmas, lady.
How are the Bahamas?
Hmm.
Hey.
Merry Christmas.
Look up.
Mistletoe alert.
Hung by moi.
Now we have no choice but to kiss.
Archie.
You are so good.
It's like you are filled with it,
and I know that I need
goodness in my life.
I need you in my life.
In other words,
I love you, too, Archie Andrews.
And so, another mystery was wrapped up
in a neat, tidy bow,
just in time for Christmas.
Throughout the Black
Hood's reign of terror,
Betty had stared into
the blackest of voids.
The place where Joseph Conway's
soul had once, perhaps existed.
And in that void, she'd
seen a dark reflection,
a truth that could not be burned away.
A truth that whispered to her,
"This isn't over."
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --