Previously on Riverdale...
You wanna get through this, you
should hang with the serpents.
You really think you
can come to my house
and there won't be any pay back?
I'm wondering when you're actually gonna
address the real problem in Riverdale,
the Southside.
We need to be united.
If we let the fear take
over, that's when we're dead.
I want a more active
role in Lodge industries.
Of course, you're a Lodge after all.
Everybody needs to leave right now!
The Black Hood's coming here.
This is from The Black Hood.
He says he's doing it for me.
- Hello.
- Hello, Betty.
This is the Black Hood speaking.
How...
How do I know this is real?
"I will strike next where it all began."
Were you there?
At the Town Hall?
Oh, yes.
But you didn't hurt anyone?
Tonight was all about you.
What do you want?
The same as you: to set Riverdale
on the righteous path again.
To cleanse it of sinners...
Isn't that what you want?
Not by killing people.
Only the ones who deserve it.
People like... your sister.
I know all about the sin
she carries in her womb.
I also know she's at a
farm, two hours North.
If you try to warn her, I'll know.
If you tell the police we've spoken
or your mystery-loving boyfriend
I'll carve her like a Jack O'Lantern.
Please, don't hurt her.
Who are you talking to? It's late.
Then don't you deny me, Betty.
It was Jughead, wasn't it?
Yeah.
You know, I gave him
the benefit of the doubt,
but now that he's
living on the Southside
amongst those criminals and degenerates,
he's showing his true colors.
No doubt, inspiring that
stunt of yours at Town Hall.
Pulling the fire alarm?
I didn't know what else to do.
Given the letter that
the Black Hood sent me.
If he even wrote it.
Sheriff Keller said something seems off.
He's gonna have it analyzed,
along with the one that I got.
In the meantime, I want you
home straight after school
- Are we clear?
- Yeah. Sorry, Mom.
I did what Weatherbee asked.
Wrote an apology letter,
and posted a new video,
apologizing some more.
So this Red Circle business, it's over,
I'm happy to hear it.
I'm missing my son.
_
I need to tell you something, Arch,
but you can't tell anyone else.
Not Veronica, not Jughead not your dad,
no one. Promise me.
Yeah, sure. I promise.
The Black Hood called me.
- What?
- Keep walking.
Wait, the Black Hood called you?
Yes. It's risky for me
to even be telling you.
But we're best friends and we
live right next door to each other
So us walking to school together,
would look perfectly normal to
anyone who might be watching.
Including him.
You think he's watching us?
I don't know, he could be.
I know it sounds crazy, but it was him.
Betty, you have to tell the
police. Even if it's not him.
It is him.
And he told me if I went to the
police, or if I told Jughead, he'd...
God, he knows where Polly is, Arch.
If he calls me again, I have to answer.
I'm not letting you
go through this alone.
"This most recent incident
confirms that the real threat
is not the Black Hood, but the
Southside and its corruptive forces.
Developer and ex-con Hiram Lodge
boasts that his SoDale project will
revitalize the forsaken neighborhood,
But this reporter speculates
Hiram Lodge doesn't
want to fix our problems,
merely profit from them."
And right before our Open
House. Thank you, Alice Cooper.
We can't let anything
derail the project.
Not Alice, not the Southside gangs,
not some hooded psychopath.
Okay, but right now, our
biggest problem is capital.
We're running out of it and fast.
I've invited potential
investors to the Open House.
The St. Clairs are
coming up from New York.
Wait. They are?
Nicky included? I haven't
seen Nicky in forever!
Yeah. He's a budding
music producer, now.
And his father is King Midas rich.
We get him to invest,
others will follow.
You wanted a seat at the table?
Nick has his father's ear.
Help us close this.
Show him all the good things
Riverdale has to offer.
With pleasure.
Nice article your
girlfriend's Mom wrote.
Yeah, I saw that.
Dilton Doiley said he was stabbed
when a bunch of you guys jumped him.
Idiot stabbed himself.
With his own knife.
And we didn't jump
him, there was a fight,
Bulldogs versus Serpents,
and you see this?
Your boy Andrews gave it to me.
Just before his girlfriend
shot a gun into the air.
What happened?
And of course, Northsiders
get off scot-free,
and the rest of us are
hauled in by the police.
It's payback time.
What are you guys talking about?
This.
What is that?
Is that a pipebomb?
Fogarty's cousin served in the Army.
He's gonna build us something.
We'll do it after hours,
but it'll shut the Riverdale
register down once and for all.
You think blowing up a building
is going to make things better?
Can't get any worse
Yeah, Sweet Pea, it can.
Let me talk to Archie. Let
me figure this out. Okay?
Man, that's your answer for everything.
Talk and more talk. And we don't
even know who you stand with.
Us? Or them?
You can't be half a Serpent.
Great. So Archie started World War III.
Northside has been
dumping on us for years.
Your dad tried to keep
the peace, avoid bloodshed.
Now that he's gone,
idiots like Sweet Pea
think there's only one
path and one solution.
Violence.
Nick and I were the "will they
or won't they?" of our jet set
He's an outrageous
flirt, but we never dated.
We'd hop from club to club,
go on these madcap adventures,
- stay up all night...
- Who's this now?
Oh, Archiekins, don't be jelly,
it's just a ghost from my
bad girl past, Nick St. Clair,
breezing into town for the Open House.
You have nothing to worry about.
I thin this Northsider's lost.
I'm not.
I'm over being half a Serpent.
Wow. You will do anything to
protect your Northside buddies.
My father was a Serpent. He led you.
I wanna stand with you guys.
Tall Boy was the one
who gave me this jacket.
It's finally time I start wearing it.
So, now you wanna be a Serpent, huh?
Let's see if you survive
the initiation first.
"Unknown."
Hello?
Your mother's at work.
Yes, she and my dad are...
I know, I'm looking at them
through a nice, big picture window.
Are you alone?
I am.
She's a thorn in both of
our sides, your mother.
We can't have her looming over us.
Wait. If you're suggesting...
Check your email.
Publish what I've sent. And
then I'll know that you're loyal.
I want something in return.
To prove your loyalty.
How about...
You do this for me. And then
you get to ask me a question.
And I have to answer it.
You have until tomorrow night.
Oh, my God. Is that...
It's my mom.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
What the hell?
Your initiation begins now.
With you assuming the
guardianship of the beast.
You've gotta be kidding me.
So, what do you think of the beast?
He stinks and he barks all the time.
He's got no boundaries.
Every new recruit has to take
care of Hot Dog. It's tradition.
By the way, this is our third Hot Dog.
Oh, Hot Dog the third?
This is getting borderline ridiculous.
Kind of like Forsyth the third?
My mom went after the Black Hood hard,
so it's no surprise he
wants to humiliate her.
We can't do it, Arch. It
would destroy her credibility.
Yeah. And build yours
with the Black Hood.
Anyway, what credibility? Your
mom's always going after our friends.
It would blindside her.
We can't publish it.
Mr. and Mrs. St. Clair.
Nicholas. On behalf of
my mother and father,
welcome to Riverdale.
While you're in town, think of
me as your "corporate concierge."
Anything you need, ask away.
How about a better hotel, to start?
Now, now, Nicholas.
It's not the Waldorf,
nor the Plaza, but,
The Five Seasons, like all of
Riverdale, it has its charms.
One charm. Veronica Lodge,
as lovely as ever.
We sent the letters to
two different specialists
but the handwriting wasn't a match.
So whoever wrote your letter was
either a copycat, or pranking you, or...
Or something much more banal
like a teenager acting
out to get attention.
What? You think I wrote it?
The cipher was cribbed
from a Nancy Drew book
of all places.
Mom, what possible reason
could I have for making this up?
I don't know, Betty. Maybe
you and your Serpent boyfriend
cooked this up because
you guys were bored.
Okay. We're not gonna
rule anything out yet,
at least not till we know
who we're dealing with.
_
"A serpent never shows cowardice."
"If a Serpent's killed or imprisoned,
their family will be taken care of."
Serpents...
Come on, focus. You need
to take this seriously.
Okay, I am, Toni, I
swear to God I am, just...
First the Beast, and now these laws.
Why the change of heart, anyway?
Why go from conscientious
objector to full-fledged member?
'Cause of something you said...
My dad was the only person that was
keeping idiots like Sweet Pea in line.
Someone needs to step up.
To keep an all-out war from erupting.
I am taking this seriously, Toni.
So from the top.
What is the fourth law?
"No serpent is left for dead."
What is the fifth law?
"A serpent never betrays its own."
What is the sixth?
"In unity, there is strength."
In unity, there is strength!
You know the laws.
Now it's time for the next trial.
Retrieve the knife.
What?
Rattlesnake, Toni.
The rattle snake bit me and drew blood.
One that had its venom glands removed.
The important thing
is you showed no fear.
You grabbed the knife and
you remembered all the laws.
Which means you're almost
a Serpant now, Juggie.
My regular, Pop. Thanks.
I don't judge you,
Alice. It was years ago.
What the hell are you talking about?
Who gave you this article?
Because I know I ripped it
out of every public archive.
Maybe it was one of the
thousands of Southsiders
you attack in your paper daily.
I mean, really, Mom, you talk
trash about FP, about Jughead,
about the Serpents when
you yourself were one.
Why would you publish that?
Revenge, plain and simple.
No, Mom. Not revenge.
Justice.
Against you and your
holier-than-thou attitude.
Betty, that is enough.
I'm so glad you two are
getting this chance to meet.
Although, your brown-nosing
at dinner was over the top.
How dare you? I love your mother's flan.
Although, I still have
room for more dessert.
Here.
No, thank you. I'm full.
Veronica Lodge turning down a bump.
What a brave new world it is.
How about it, Big Red?
So, what is it that you
country mice do for fun up here?
Catch lightning bugs in mason jars?
- No, we...
- Basically.
Ronnie,
what kind of kink is this?
I wear them when I'm plm ing
with Josie and the Pussycats.
- You're in a band?
- Mmm-hmm.
Called the Pussycats?
Just when I thought you
couldn't possibly get any sexier.
Hello?
How did it feel, Betty?
Knocking your mother of her high horse?
We had a deal.
What's your question?
And it can't be my name.
The face under the hood...
Would I recognize it?
Yes.
Do you feel closer to me now?
I do. I feel as if we're friends.
But I'm selfish, Betty. I don't
like sharing you with other people.
So I need you to cut
them out of your life,
or I will, my way.
Let's start with that
daughter of a philanderer,
and an embezzler, complicit
in her father's crimes...
Veronica's not...
She's innocent.
Oh, Betty,
you don't really believe that.
Betty Cooper.
You are a sight for sore eyes.
Thanks for coming to meet me.
God, I've missed you, I just...
I'm feeling... I don't know...
Unmoored.
Me, too.
I just wanted to make
sure you were still alive.
What do you mean?
That expose that you published
about your mom, that article.
Oh, um...
That's a long story,
but yeah, pretty intense.
What happened to your hand?
I'm dogsitting.
You remember Hot Dog, that mutt?
Don't worry, he's got the shots.
I wish we could just go.
Just hop on the motorcycle
and just leave Riverdale.
Go someplace where there's
no Northside, or Southside,
or Serpents, Ghoulies...
No...
Crazy moms, no Black Hoods.
Like Romeo and Juliet, but we
live happily ever after instead.
You Pussycats are pearls
before the swine of Riverdale.
You all have to come to the
party I'm hosting tonight
in your honor.
Let's say ten o'clock, my
hotel room at the Five Seasons.
Did somebody say party?
Hi, there.
I'm Riverdale's Resident
It Girl, Cheryl Blossom.
You must be Veronica's old
school chum I keep hearing about
Nick St. Clair.
Now that's a name I can get behind.
Ten o'clock, you said?
I'll be there at 11:00.
Betty.
What's up?
I uh... I went by your
house this morning,
to walk you to school, but your
mom said you'd already left.
Did he call you again?
No, he didn't.
Betty...
My old friend Nick here
is having a little soiree
at his hotel tonight. Will you come?
Betty's my bestie and the best.
I won't take no for an answer.
I wouldn't miss it.
And then, we walk into the Gilded Lily,
and there's Gal! Again!
"Gal"?
Gadot. Keep up, Archie.
Archiekins. A refill, s'il vous plait?
Forget the teetotaling.
Let's move on to something
with a little more kick.
- Is that...
- Jinglejangle? Why, yes. It is.
- I hooked him up.
- Tasters? Who's up first?
Dude, we told you, we're not...
Archie, don't take this the wrong way,
but you are an epic buzzkill.
Come on, Vee.
Like back in the day.
Aren't you supposed to
be showing me a good time?
Per Daddy's orders?
Down, Nicky, I'm just getting going.
And now that you mention it,
I, in fact, wouldn't mind a little
sugar to spice up this party.
What?
Every other night it's
burgers and milkshakes.
Can't we just cut loose and
pretend we're normal, for once?
- I'm in.
- Me, too.
Kevin?
Pussycats, care to partake?
- Betty?
- No, thanks.
- Come on, it'll be fun.
- I said no, Vee.
Okay, relax, Betty, this
is strictly voluntary.
Perhaps we should decamp to the bedroom,
so as not to corrupt the country mice.
You know what? I
changed my mind. I'm in.
Bravo, Archie Andrews!
There's that good, strong Riverdale
stock I've been jonesing for!
Come on, Betty, don't
be such a wallflower!
You're boyfriendless for
a night! Have some fun!
Like you, you mean?
I was gonna say you're
making a fool of yourself.
Acting like some privileged,
shallow, airhead party girl.
Excuse me?
Yeah.
I mean, it's all recycled banter
and plunging necklines and
throwing shade to distract us
all from the fact that there's
really nothing going on underneath...
- Betty, what the hell are you saying?
- What we're all thinking.
That the only reason Veronica
hangs out with us is circumstance.
She's not our friend.
The minute someone from
her trashy past shows up,
she starts using us for
drugs or music or distraction,
and why should we be surprised?
Like father, like daughter, right?
You better shut it down, Betty.
Or what, Veronica?
You'll have your dad put a hit on me?
Or maybe you'll do it yourself,
because you may have fooled
all of them, but not me.
Try to reform all you want, but
you're a bad person, Veronica.
You'll always be a bad person.
Why don't you just go,
then, if I'm such a monster?
- Veronica...
- I'm fine.
Obviously, she's not.
What? You wanna go
after her, be my guest.
But I'll be damned if I'm
chasing Betty down after that...
Whatever it was.
In fact, Reggie?
Turn the music up, will you?
What's up?
Jughead, I, um...
I came to warn you, I guess.
If you're having second thoughts,
now would be the time to back out
because the final trial,
is on a whole other level.
"The Gauntlet", you mean?
If it's anything like the
Beast, I think I'll be fine.
It's whatever.
No, Jughead, it's not "whatever."
You join us, you gotta
be willing to die for us.
Because we will for you.
And your Northside
friends? Your girlfriend?
You're gonna look up one day,
and they're all gonna be gone,
because that's what happens
when you join a gang.
The Serpents are no exception.
Consider me warned, thank you, Toni.
Never has one of my parties
fizzled out so spectacularly.
I don't know what got into Betty.
She's my best friend, believe it or not.
Those things that she said,
you're not a bad person, Veronica.
In fact, you're incredible.
You're smart, vivacious.
You're sexy.
Nick, I'm sorry if I gave
you the wrong impression.
- I'm with Archie.
- Oh, come on, Vee.
You barely looked at that
hayseed yokel all night.
You were all over me.
Nick, we're friends, we're old friends.
Nick, I mean it, stop!
Same old Veronica, huh?
You flirt and you tease, but in the end,
you think you're better than me.
You're a pig.
With the power to implode this
pathetic deal your criminal father's
so desperately trying to make happen.
So unless you want that to go away,
I'd be thinking of ways you might
start showing me some appreciation.
If you need help, I
can suggest a couple...
I did it.
But now I want my question,
- what will make you stop?
- You.
As long as you continue
showing me your devotion.
I can't keep doing this...
I'm sure you can.
Jughead.
- The son of a Serpent.
- No.
He's not worthy of your love.
Cut him out of your life...
Or I will.
What the hell was that last night?
- Betty...
- I lied to you.
When you asked me if the Black
Hood had called again. He did.
And he told me to cut Veronica
out of my life or he'd...
And now he wants me to do
the same with Jughead...
Betty, why didn't you tell me?
Because I knew you'd
try to talk me out of it.
You're right.
It's my mistake.
Archie, put the phone
down! Put the phone down!
Listen to me.
He hasn't attacked or killed
anyone since we started talking.
I think this is distracting him.
Betty, he's torturing you.
Making you hurt your mom,
Veronica and now Jughead?
How are you gonna put him
and yourself through that?
I was hoping maybe you would do it.
What?
Maybe you could tell
him that we just need
to stay away from
each other for a while.
Something, anything,
to just keep him away...
To appease the Black Hood.
- Betty.
- It doesn't have to be cruel, Archie,
just enough to make Jug believe it.
We can walk it back later.
You mean, you hope we can.
No. We can.
And we will.
Please, Archie.
Don't quit on me now.
Hey, so great to see you.
- Thank you for coming.
- Glad to see you.
Oh, well, if this turnout doesn't
convince the St. Clairs to invest,
I don't know what will.
Hey, mija. How'd it go with Nick?
Why, did he say something?
No, we haven't seen him.
But from all reports,
your charm offensive is
paying off. Good work.
Oh, there's Nick now.
Oh, looks like we're
running low on canapes.
Excuse me while I go
quietly yell at the caterer.
And I have a partner to wrangle.
Yeah.
The whole point of this
Open House is to socialize.
Figured I'd leave that to the pros.
You're not without your
charms, Fred Andrews.
We're glad you're back at work.
We, huh?
Hiram Lodge. It's been
a long time, buddy.
Yeah. Glad you could make it.
- Hey, my pleasure.
- Where's Alice?
Well, between us, that
mugshot took a toll on her.
So we both decided, it'd be better
if I covered the event alone.
Well, we'd love to have you
standing with us up on that stage.
I mean, hell, you built it.
That's true.
Oh, my God!
- Alice.
- Shove it, Hal.
You're gonna need to
top this off, thank you.
Before you throw a drink in my face,
I'm sorry.
I crossed the line.
You obliterated a line.
I strongly concur,
and it's not an excuse,
but over the last three
months, I've been...
in and out of rehab.
It's been... a struggle.
Obviously.
Last night was messy,
but we've all been there.
So, why don't we start over
with two glasses of ginger ale.
I'll drink to that.
- Archie...
- We gotta talk, Jug.
Uh, now is really not a good time, okay?
You need to leave, okay? You gotta go.
Why, what's going on?
What the hell do we have here?
- Just leave him, all right?
- Wait.
You're friends with these thugs?
It's not what you think.
Are you joining the Serpents?
If he survives, and go ahead
and call us thugs one more time.
Jughead, these are the
guys who attacked me.
Who attacked Reggie, and
Veronica and Dilton. Your friends.
Wait, is that why you're here?
- To warn me?
- No.
I came here to tell you
to stay away from Betty.
She doesn't want to see you anymore.
Screw you, I just saw Betty yesterday...
- She was fine.
- No, dude.
She's been wanting to
break up with you for weeks.
She's been agonizing over it.
Since you crossed the dark side,
she couldn't bring herself to do it.
So, she sent you?
Betty would never do that!
If you don't believe me, then call her.
And feel free to tell her
you're a Serpent now, too.
I bet she'll love that.
She saw where you were headed, Jughead.
We all did and she knows you
can't be with them and with her.
Come on, man.
You know it, too.
Tell Betty I got the message.
Yeah.
What? Did you enjoy the show?
The show hasn't even started yet.
We didn't get much of a
chance to talk last night.
I'm choosing to blame
Betty's Britneyesque meltdown.
I'll let you make it up to me.
Pour moi?
Merci.
Ladies and gentlemen. A new
story begins in Riverdale tonight.
A story about reinvention
and aspiration.
This building will be the
first chapter of that story.
Luxury apartments, shopping,
and even a golf course.
The Southside as we know it will
be gone, replaced with a new Eden.
So let us raise our glasses
to a brighter tomorrow.
Today, let's celebrate
with a little music.
♪ What's the time? ♪
♪ Well, it's gotta
be close to midnight ♪
♪ My body's talkin' to me ♪
♪ It says, "Time for danger" ♪
♪ It says "I wanna commit a crime ♪
♪ Wanna be The cause of a fight ♪
♪ I wanna put on a tight skirt ♪
♪ And flirt with a stranger" ♪
♪ I've had a knack From way back ♪
♪ At breaking the rules
Once I learn the game ♪
♪ Get up! Life's too quick
I know someplace sick ♪
♪ Where this chick'll
dance In the flames ♪
♪ We don't need any money ♪
♪ I always get in for free ♪
♪ You can get in, too ♪
♪ If you get in with me ♪
♪ Let's go out tonight ♪
♪ Meow ♪
You all right?
I'm fine... I just need some air.
Is that all you got?
♪ You wanna play Let's run away ♪
♪ We won't be back Before
it's New Year's Day ♪
♪ Take me out tonight ♪
Get off of her!!
♪ In the evening I've got to roam ♪
♪ Can't sleep in the
city Of neon and chrome ♪
♪ Feels too damn much Like home ♪
♪ When the Spanish babies cry ♪
♪ So let's find a bar ♪
♪ So dark we forget who we are ♪
♪ Where all the scars ♪
♪ From the nevers And maybes die ♪
♪ Let's go out tonight ♪
♪ Don't forsake me Out tonight ♪
♪ Tonight, tonight ♪
Is it done?
Yes.
Ask me your question.
There's only one I care about now.
You want to know who I am...
Well, here's an abandoned
house on the edge of Fox Forest
at the end of the Service Road.
You'll find your answer there.
I'm here.
Do you see it?
Yes.
It's the answer to your question.
Put it on.
- Why?
- Put it on and you'll see.
- It's on.
- Now, turn around.
Why are you doing this to me?
To show you that we're the same.
Hey.
Archie? I can't...
Come to the Pembrooke. It's
Cheryl. Something bad happened.
What?
If you hadn't come when you did...
Where the hell is he?
You can put your cape away, Archie.
The Pussycats already saved me.
I feel so sick about this.
Nick's a monster.
And there's no way he hasn't done this
before. Probably right under my nose.
It's not your fault, Veronica.
I wanna press charges.
I want Nick to pay.
To suffer.
To burn in hell.
Welcome to the Serpents.
Officially.
You're gonna have a hard
time hiding that from Betty.
I think it's a non-issue now.
I wasn't sure if you
were going to call again.
There's one piece of
unfinished business.
What's that?
The fact that you've been
telling Archie about our chats.
Betty, I've been watching you...
You never said I couldn't tell Archie.
You broke the rules, Betty,
and now your sister will pay.
Please don't hurt her.
Then give me another name.
- Right now.
- What?
If you want to save your
sister, give me another name.
The name of someone guilty.
Come on, Betty.
One little name.
I won't, I can't do that...
Then I'll kill your sister.
And your mother and your father,
and everyone you hold dear.
Nick St. Clair.
He's staying at the Five Seasons.
I told you we were the same.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --