Previously on Riverdale...
- The Conway murders?
- They were a family of five.
I found justice.
What if Mr. Svenson
wasn't the Black Hood?
The real Black Hood
could still be alive.
My Dad might be the Black Hood.
I don't know. I've seen your
father sneak around Thistlehouse...
Lodge is a problem.
Did you have anything to do
with Papa Poutine's death?
His son Small Fry is
looking for payback.
Penny, you wanna deal drugs?
It's not gonna be with the Serpents.
That used to be my Serpent tattoo.
- You're nuts!
- She will be back.
Our old adversaries, the
Ghoulies, have been released.
Word on the street is that
they want Serpent blood.
- Midge?
- You're dead, Vixen killer!
Mr. Fogarty, we need
you to come with us.
- I din't kill her.
- Didn't you?
His release is going to make a lot
of people in this town very unhappy.
The Circle is officially disbanded.
You're not the one paying us. Hiram is.
Fangs Fogarty is being released.
What?
Well, they wanna rip Fangs
apart. We need your help, Archie!
Okay, Dad. Let's talk.
I swear, Mother, if this is
one of your gentlemen callers...
I suggest you run whilst you still can.
I only miss when I mean to.
Help us! We need a doctor.
- Ma'am.
- Wait your turn, please.
- He was shot!
- I need you to step back...
- He's dying!
- Hey, what's gong on here?
My friend was shot right in the stomach.
Hey, get me a gurney.
Here, here, here.
Lift up, lift up.
Let's go.
Hang in there, hang in there.
Jug, where do you think you're going?
To find the guy who shot Fangs!
You're not going out there.
Not with people rioting.
Look, you're angry, you
want justice. So do I.
But you've got a fallen
soldier here, boy,
and we need to talk to his family.
- It's part of being a leader.
- Some leader I am.
Don't go down that road.
All right, come on. Come on.
Oh.
Cheryl.
The Black Hood just
attacked me at Thistlehouse.
Oh, my God.
Was it my dad?
Based on waistline alone,
it could've been him, yes.
Luckily, I was able to get to
my archery set and hunting cape.
- You didn't kill him, did you?
- No.
I shot to wound, hit him
in the right shoulder.
He's fled into the woods,
where I plan to track him.
But just in case he escapes
my clutches, be forewarned.
Now that he's a maimed animal,
he's operating on instinct,
ready to lash out and
kill anyone in his path,
even his loved ones.
Here, include that.
Elizabeth, thank goodness.
Mom, are you okay? Have you seen Dad?
He's out covering the
riot. Honey, where are you?
The streets aren't safe.
You need to get here.
I'm on my way, but stay put, okay?
I'm not going anywhere. It's
a big night for The Register.
If it bleeds, it leads.
Get over here now.
- Hey, Arch...
- It's just me, Mr. Andrews.
I was about to slip
out. Is something wrong?
On the news, it said a riot broke
out down at the Sheriff's Station.
Where is Archie?
- Where the hell is Reggie?
- I thought he was with you.
We got separated when
the fight broke out.
Guys, Reggie had a gun.
He didn't shoot Fangs, though.
I tackled him before he could.
Why would Reggie have a gun?
I can guess who put
the idea in his head.
But right now, we just gotta find him.
Some of the Serpents
saw Reggie with the gun.
They're gonna go after him.
Kev, Moose, we'll
head to Reggie's house.
Everyone else, fan out,
call if you find him.
Archie was there when
that Serpent got shot.
- I don't know what he's caught up in.
- I'm coming with you.
Good evening, Mr. Andrews.
I'm here to pick up, Ms. Lodge.
Thank you, Andre. Yes,
bring her directly home.
Okay.
Now that we know Veronica's safe,
one of Minetta's deputies will
take you over to The Register.
Alice is waiting for your announcement.
Well, there's no way of
controlling what could happen.
Hiram, it's a huge gamble.
No, the fire's started, mi
amor. Chaos is good for us.
We have the pieces in place
to restore order and safety.
Fred doesn't. Andre will
keep watch on Veronica.
- Where will you be?
- Out with another deputy.
Hiram?
You're not keeping
anything from me, right?
Don't start doubting me now, mi amor.
Excuse me, ma'am. How's Fangs Fogarty?
He's still in surgery.
I'll want to talk to him
as soon as he wakes up.
Sheriff Minetta...
Shouldn't you be on the street
looking for who shot Fangs?
There's already a manhunt underway.
Your little Serpent pals aren't
making things easy, though.
Rioting, carousing, terrorizing the
neighborhood. Already arrested a few.
Fangs wouldn't have a slug in his gut if
you'd done your job in the first place.
I don't know the details
of your parole, Mr. Jones,
but I'm certain harassing an
officer would violate them.
Jug?
Mr. Lodge, it's me, Reggie.
I need your help. Someone
shot Fangs. It wasn't me.
But I was there and now the
Southsiders think I did it.
That's unfortunate, Reggie,
but I'm afraid I can't help you.
Oh, my God, is that Mrs. Klump?
Andre, stop the car!
That's Midge's mom.
Ms. Veronica, wait.
Mrs. Klump?
Are you okay?
I may have killed that boy.
Archie, what the hell is going on?
- The Serpents are going nuts.
- Yeah.
Reggie shot Fangs!
No, dude, I was with Reggie
when it happened, it wasn't him.
So you need to call off your crew.
- We're just leaving Reggie's house now.
- Did they find him?
No, he wasn't home. We're
headed to the high school now.
That's where Mrs. Mantle
said they were going.
Okay, I'm on my way.
Whenever you're ready, Hermione.
As a mayoral candidate,
I feel it's important to take
charge in times of crisis.
Like this riot, which I believe
is brought about by the
actions of the Black Hood.
Which is why I would
like to offer a bounty.
$1 million to whoever can
deliver the Black Hood.
Alive or preferably, dead.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
A bounty?
What are you talking
about? Is that even legal?
The Black Hood is an active
shooter on the streets of Riverdale.
He tried to kill one of your classmate
outside the Sheriff's Station.
No, no. The Black Hood
did not shoot Fangs.
Excuse me, young lady?
How would you know that?
Did anyone actually see the Black
Hood at the Sheriff's station?
And why exactly are you being
protective of a murderer?
Cheryl, any new leads?
- Where are you right now?
- I'm at The Register, why?
He's exited the forest and he's
headed for the houses beyond the pines.
Maybe even yours.
- I have to go.
- Wait, cousin.
Do not go into that house alone.
I have to find my dad
before anyone else does.
Otherwise, he's a dead man walking.
That's gotta be the Southsiders.
Serpent scum!
Settle down, Moose. We're
out manned and unarmed.
I'm not just gonna hide here
while they trash our school!
- I'm with Moose.
- All right.
But it's us three against
who knows how many.
So if we're gonna do
this, we gotta gear up.
Ronnie, can I call you back?
I'm kinda busy, a riot broke out.
Yes, Archie, I know. I was
just out in the middle of it.
What? I thought you
were still at my house?
Not only did I brave the streets,
I delivered Fangs's shooter,
Mrs. Klump, to the authorities.
- Mrs. Klump shot Fangs?
- Can you blame her?
I gotta go, Ronnie, I gotta tell
the Serpents, but I love you.
I love you, too.
Mom?
Sheriff Minetta?
Veronica, what are you doing here?
You're supposed to
be at home with Andre.
Andre's in the car, We
had to make a detour.
Good Lord, Mom!
Are you and Daddy trying to
turn Riverdale into Gotham City?
Serpents, stop!
Well, Fellas, looks like we
found some bulldogs to put down.
Sweet Pea, I swear, Reggie didn't
shoot Fangs. It was Mrs. Klump.
Bull. I saw Mantle with the gun!
Then you also saw me tackle
him, before he got a shot off!
It was Midge's mom!
She's down at the station.
Yeah, and Fangs is
still clinging to life.
And whether it was Reggie or
Mrs. Klump who pulled the trigger,
a Northsider put him there.
You took our friend, our land...
And you'll take everything
if we give you the chance.
So now you get to watch
as we burn your school to the ground.
What the hell do you boys
think you're doing to my school?
Hello? Dad?
Dad...
You're too late, Jughead.
Well, you try Mad Max-ing
your way through a riot.
- What happened in the school?
- Weatherbee shut us down.
- And kicked our asses out.
- Then the Serpents took off again.
- Do you know where?
- Yeah, they went down Fernleaf.
- Probably to Midge Klump's house.
- Why there?
To trash it. Because I told them
Mrs. Klump shot Fangs, not Reggie.
Jughead, you have to
coax them off the ledge.
- Yeah, I'm on it.
- Wait...
- You spoken to Betty?
- She's with her mom.
Keep in touch.
You, too.
- Hello.
- Archie, it's Pop.
I've got a friend of yours here.
I think he needs help.
Hello?
Betty, it's FP.
I'm at Riverdale
General, is Jug with you?
Mr. Jones, no, I... I
don't know where he is.
All right, if you see him, you
tell him I'm looking for him, okay?
- Of course, I will.
- Also, uh...
Betty, they just brought
your old man into the ER.
My dad?
Is he hurt badly?
I don't know. He's bleeding quite
a bit. You want me to check on him?
No. That's okay, Mr.
Jones. I'm on my way.
Where do you plan on
getting the million dollars
to pay for this lunatic bounty?
Your father has secret funds.
My ass, he does.
And if Daddy thinks he can use my money
for one of his Machiavellian
ploys, he better think again.
Because I'm taking back what
I got from the St. Clairs.
Your father already told you he'd
put that money in a trust for you!
He stole it, you mean!
Veronica!
You're wasting your time.
Your money is not in there.
Veronica, just open the door
and we can talk about this.
I didn't know where else to
go. Mr. Lodge left me hanging.
Wait, Reggie, I know he paid
you to trash the Whyte Wyrm.
But did he put you up to this?
Guys? Outside.
Sepents! They're coming for me.
Archie, what's up?
Jughead, where the hell are you guys?
I just got the Serpents
back to the Whyte Wyrm.
Mrs. Klump's house is secure.
What's wrong?
Well, if the Serpents are with you,
then who the hell is out here at Pop's?
Oh, crap.
Jug?
That's right, I'm here.
Looks like the Ghoulies
are back in town.
Damm it! Nobody's answering
at the Sheriff's station.
Looks like we're on our own.
Okay, we should be fine
as long as everybody...
Everybody, get away from the windows!
Stay down!
Do you have a gun in here, Pop?
No.
Had my fill of gunfire back in the war.
But I learned a trick
in the riots of '79.
I have Mr. Lodge's leftover
liquor from that poker night.
And you get to the roof
through the crawlspace...
I like how you're thinking, Pop.
Anyone want to come out and play?
We got some new toys to show you!
Hey!
Come on.
Hit me!
All right, now it's a party!
Come on, let's go. Let's go!
Get the hell outta here.
Mr. Keller, I thought you resigned.
Turned in my badge,
but not the cruiser yet.
How did you guys know we were here?
Well, Jug called, said you were
in trouble so I called your dad...
right when Kevin called.
We're not letting this town
go down without a fight.
Hot Riverdale Dads to the Rescue.
I can't just sit here...
You don't have a choice,
Sweet Pea, you're staying put.
You said it yourself,
the Ghoulies are back!
We will deal with them.
As soon as my dad gets back...
Oh, so you're not our
leader all of a sudden?
Oh, no, that's right, you're
just the guy who got Fangs shot!
- Watch it...
- And now, Fangs might die!
And the Ghoulies are out for our blood
because of a drag race you started.
An hour. That's all I'm
asking for, Sweet Pea.
This is utterly vile. Daddy
has already written the story.
About the affair you and Fred
had. What was he planning to do?
Publish that in The Register?
And drag you both through the mud?
Fred's running on family values.
I'm the law and order candidate.
Your father believes an October Surprise
like this one would
hurt me, but I'd survive.
And it would utterly
destroy Fred's campaign.
Wait, you're in on this?
There's a game plan, Veronica.
What kind of man would
do this to his own wife?
I'll tell you! The kind of man
who always has someone
else to take the risk,
to stand in the line of
fire, to run for Mayor.
That's what you are to him.
A means to an end.
Kindling for the fire.
Oh, no, Veronica.
Your father would never
put us in harm's way.
The fact that you still believe
that after everything he's done,
chills me, Mom.
Pop Tate, I heard there was
an incident at the diner.
Rioters were here, Mr. Lodge.
But Fred Andrews showed up
with Tom Keller and FP Jones.
They saved us, helped defend the
Chock'lit Shoppe from the Ghoulies.
- Everyone's calling them heroes.
- I see.
Well, thank you, Pop.
- And, uh, I'm glad you're okay.
- All right.
Sorry, we're not serving right now.
So that wasn't Hiram Lodge you
were just speaking with, was it?
- It was.
- He's an old friend of my father's.
You wouldn't happen to know
where he lives, would you?
Excuse me?
Um, my dad is here. Hal
Cooper, what room is he in?
Uh, 221. Just down the hall.
Dad?
Oh.
We keep missing each other.
You murdered Dr. Masters?
He asked too many questions.
So there's no method to the
killing, now? No grand design?
You're just a run-of-the-mill psychopath?
You need to come home, Betty.
So we can talk and finish this.
Fine.
You don't scare me.
Your mother's here.
What? Mom's there?
If you're not home in 10 minutes,
or if you call the police,
I will slit your mother's throat
in the middle of the living room.
No.
- Hello.
- Hello, lover boy.
It's your old gal pal.
Penny?
You picked a really bad time.
Oh, I heard.
Riverdale, burning to
the ground? It's tragic.
How about we meet up
and talk about it, hmm?
Your old hangout, by the docks?
Why the hell would I do that?
Because if you don't, I'll start
carving up your girlfriend's face.
Betty?
Oh, please. Ponytail's a snooze!
No, I mean your Southside Smurfette.
What do you think I should start with?
Tell her to go to hell, Jughead.
Hmm, maybe her tongue, huh?
Come now. And alone.
It'll just be me and Pinkie here.
- Mom? Mom, where are you?
- Oh.
Betty, thank God you're okay.
- I've been calling you. Where have you been?
- Mom, is Dad here?
- Quick, is he here or is he not? Where is he?
- Yeah, honey. Why?
- What... What's going on?
- We have to go.
- What?
- We have to leave.
- We have to go.
- Betty!
You made it home.
You dad has some crazy idea
to show us old home movies.
I figured we'd indulge him since
we're practically on lock-down anyway.
What's wrong?
Well, I'm just happy
we're all here as a family.
Sit down, Betty.
I think you're really
going to enjoy this.
Now, remember, I'm making this movie
so we never forget what
your daddy sacrificed for us.
You do love your daddy,
don't you, Harold?
Yes, Mom.
And you want your daddy
to keep living with us?
Yes, Mom.
I don't understand,
what are we watching?
- Is that you, Hal?
- It is.
Your daddy did something
very noble, Harold.
He took care of that Conway family.
They were sinners. And
what happens to sinners?
Sinners have to die.
Oh, my God!
What is this, a snuff film?
Shut the hell up, Alice,
for once in your life!
That's right.
Now, That little
Conway boy who survived,
they're going to ask him
who killed his family.
He needs to point out somebody,
anybody, but not Daddy.
Because we don't want Daddy to
be taken away from us, do we?
No, I love my daddy.
So you have to help him.
Make sure that when
they ask the Conway boy
who he saw kill his family,
make sure he doesn't say Daddy.
Can you do that, Harold? Convince him?
I think so.
You're a good boy, Hal.
Your father let him escape,
but you, you will do better.
You must do better.
Take out your taperecorder, Alice.
I need you to record this.
The Conways, that was the family
that was murdered 40 years ago?
Yes. Oh, my God!
Take it out!
And I want to tell my story.
No, our story, really.
First, to clear something up.
Your Great-Grandpappy Cooper wasn't
murdered by his brother, like some dog.
He was the killer.
He killed Great-Grandpappy Blossom
and then took on the Cooper name to
create a new identity for himself.
For us.
What does that have
to do with the Conways?
The Conways knew our secret.
And Mr. Conway blackmailed
my father, your Grandpappy.
Them? The Conways knew our secret.
- They were sinners, Betty.
- Even the children?
Well, there was one survivor.
The Conways' boy, Joseph.
Mr. Svenson, who you convinced
to accuse an innocent man.
Joseph was easy to man manipulate
as a boy and as a man.
What are you telling us? Hal, that...
That I have a darkness, Alice.
The same darkness my father had,
the same darkness his father had.
And now, it lives in Betty.
Our daughter.
Who am I, Betty?
Say it.
Say who I am!
You're the Black Hood.
That's right.
Now say what I did.
You...
shot Mr. Andrews.
You killed Ms. Grundy,
the Sugarman, Midge, Dr. Masters...
- But the debate...
- Was not me.
I can't take credit for that.
How's Veronica dealing with all this?
Oh, she's in lock-down at the Pembrooke.
For all of Mr. Lodge's
talk about law and order,
he was nowhere to be seen tonight.
Well, I just went out
there to try to find you.
I'm gonna take a shower.
I'm gonna lock up.
You okay?
Thought about going
pro after high school.
- Dad!
- What? Okay...
No!
Dad, Dad!
I'm good.
Tom Keller, he just put these
on before we went to the diner.
I'm good.
Archie, no!
Dad, why did you become the Black Hood?
'Cause this is a town of sinners, Betty.
And...
Sinners have to die.
Your speech at the Jubilee.
Riverdale must do better.
We must do better.
You will do better. You must do better.
Reminded me of a promise
that I'd made to my mother.
That this town will do better.
We must do better.
So I picked up my father's sword,
and I continued the work that
he and my grandfather started.
The purging of sin.
No, none of this makes any sense.
Dad, why did you want
all of this recorded?
I want everyone to
understand when they find us.
Hi, Jones.
Toni, are you okay?
Jughead, she's not alone.
Surprise!
You said it was just
going to be the two of us.
I never go anywhere
without back-up any more,
not after what you did to me.
Besides, we need to talk,
all of us...
There's nothing to talk about.
I'm taking Toni and we're leaving.
Not so fast!
I've been waiting to see
you again for a long time.
Get back, you hobgoblin!
I brought back-up, too.
Like I said, I'm taking
Toni, and we're leaving.
Untie her, you Serpent hag.
Take her, then.
But remember, when all your friends
are dead, I tried giving you a chance.
Why do you keep coming
back? What do you want?
The Southside.
There's money to be made
here in "The Town With Pep,"
if you're not afraid of
getting your hands dirty.
So you're partnering with the Ghoulies
to sell drugs on the Southside?
Bingo. So here's the offer
I want you to take back
to your dad and your tribe.
The Serpents ship out tonight,
or it's a showdown with the
Ghoulies at Pickens Park at dawn.
I'm fine either way.
Hello. I'm here to see Mr. Lodge.
I'm sorry, he's not available.
Are his lovely wife and
beautiful daughter at home?
This is a game of nerves, Veronica,
and clearly, you've lost yours.
I'd rather have lost
my nerve than my mind,
which clearly, you and Daddy have.
That "October Surprise" wouldn't
just destroy Fred's campaign,
it would ruin his life!
Oh, God, who is it?
You may know my father. Goes
by the name Papa Poutine.
He told me, if he was
ever to be murdered,
not to take the life of
the man who killed him,
but to take the lives of
those that man loved the most.
- Mom...
- Mija, run. Run!
Stay behind me!
It's time we end the Ghoulie scourge
and that traitor, Penny
Peabody permanently.
Sweet Pea, two hours ago your
fight was with Reggie Mantle.
Now you want us to go
to war over territory
that we don't even control anymore?
This is Hiram Lodge's problem, not ours.
So you're just gonna hand
over Sunnyside Trailer Park,
our home to Penny and the Ghoulies?
Toni, I don't want us to die.
A rumble with the Ghoulies right now?
- It's a suicide-run.
- It's better than a coward's death.
- Don't we have to defend ourselves?
- Calm yourself...
That's enough!
I just got a call from
the Sheriff's office.
Fangs, uh...
He didn't make it. He's gone.
Fangs is dead?
And we will mourn him,
hell yeah, we will.
But first, we will honor him.
From what I just heard, it sounds
like we need to put it to a vote.
All those against going
to war with the Ghoulies?
And all those for giving them
hell on the battlefield tomorrow?
Well, Hal, I can't say I'm surprised.
Mom?
I always knew you were a Mama's boy.
- What did you say?
- You heard me.
I knew it. I knew you couldn't
do anything for yourself.
Mom, whatever you're doing, I wouldn't.
All I'm doing is I'm pointing out that
your father can't do anything right.
Not even be a serial killer!
Cleansing the town of sin?
Really, Hal, you're the damn sinner.
Mom...
What are you going to do, Hal? Are
you going to kill the entire town?
Whoever's jaywalked? What did Fred
Andrews do to deserve to get shot?
He was an adulterer.
Oh, then why don't you kill yourself?
You had a fling with Penelope Blossom.
Or me, for that matter, since
I stepped out on you with FP,
who, in every way that you're not...
is a real man.
This is a mistake.
You can see that, right?
We'd be going in blind, Dad.
Would you listen to me for two seconds?
For all we know, the Ghoulies
outnumber us one hundred to one...
Don't you think I know that?
Boy, I've been doing this
a lot longer than you have.
And we voted.
If we're going down,
we're going down fighting.
As for being outnumbered,
I'll rally the reserves.
They'll fight.
- This is Hiram.
- Fangs getting arrested, the riot,
the Ghoulies showing up the night
of the riot, with Penny in tow...
None of this is happenstance.
Jughead, I genuinely have no
idea what you're talking about.
You've been buying up
everything you could.
But you couldn't buy us,
so you paid the Ghoulies
and Penny to go to war with the Serpents
to finally get rid of
us once and for all.
How much is this costing you?
I'm hanging up now.
'Cause I have a counter offer.
Mr. Lodge?
I'm listening.
Andre?
Veronica? Hermione?
There's another dead body in the study.
It's your mess, Daddy. You clean it up.
It was him, Arch.
My dad was the Black Hood.
How did you...
Did you see him leave my house?
He tried to shoot my dad again.
When?
An hour ago.
No, no, no. That's impossible,
he was here with us.
- Jug?
- Betty...
I'm happy to hear your voice.
Me, too, Jug. You have no idea.
I just want to let you
know that I love you.
And I'll never stop loving you.
What are you saying, Jug? Where are you?
- Where is he?
- I'll see you soon.
The Sacrificial Lamb arrives.
I'll remind you of the deal that
I made with your boss, Hiram Lodge.
I hand myself over to you tonight
and there's no bloodshed tomorrow.
Apparently, getting
you out of the picture
is more important to him than
all-out Serpent annihilation.
30-to-1. Are you that afraid of me?
The only scary thing is what we're going
to do to your girlfriend
when we find her.
You're a true hero, Jughead.
Let your dying thought be that
your sacrifice was for nothing.
And that come morning, Riverdale
as you know it will cease to exist.
Don't finish him off yet, guys.
I want my pound of flesh first.
Betty, are you and your mom okay?
Mr. Jones, is Jughead with you?
- No, he's at the trailer. Why?
- I'm just really worried about him.
He called to say how much he loves me
and it almost sounded like he
was saying goodbye for good.
Toni, where was Penny hiding out?
Jug!
Sheriff Minetta delivered the
bodies to the coroner's office,
tagged them as riot victims, so no one's
going to be asking us any questions.
I am so sorry.
I just thank God that
neither of you were hurt.
I found your October Surprise file.
Well, your mother understands
the costs of winning.
Better than almost anyone.
Isn't that right, mi amor?
I realized something.
There will always be an
October surprise with you.
And another and another.
But while Mom may volunteer
to be your collateral damage,
- I won't.
- What'd I always teach you?
Never lose sight of the bigger picture.
I'm not the one who's lost sight, Daddy.
- Where is he? Where's Jug?
- Guys...
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --