[narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
Archie Andrews.
I'm Special Agent Adams with the FBI.
We believe Hiram Lodge is conducting
criminal activity.
You are at a unique position
to help us take him down.
I need assurance from you.
No matter what happens to Mr. Lodge
- my dad is gonna be okay.
- I can protect your father.
Effective immediately,
Southside High School is shut down.
- Well, it's done.
- After a few weeks, we'll quietly go about
purchasing the land
beneath Southside High.
And you will get your sizable donation
to your reelection campaign.
And, Daddy, this is...
Archie Andrews. The boy
who's captured my daughter's heart.
- I hope we can respect each other.
- Of course, Mr. Lodge.
No more sneaking
into my daughter's bedroom.
Ever.
You wanted me to get a job, and I did.
Providing comfort and companionship
to the lonely men of Riverdale.
You remember that baby
my mom put up for adoption?
- Hey, let go of my brother!
- [screams]
You'll be safe here.
[Jughead] One week after Riverdale High's
absorption of its Southside counterpart,
and everything was the same.
And nothing was the same.
Take Archie Andrews.
On the surface,
he's getting ready for basketball tryouts,
as he does every winter.
But underneath, he was churning.
His life in chaos
after an unexpected visit from the feds.
Meanwhile, the town was preparing
to honor its founding father,
General Augustus Pickens.
Mr. Jones. Eyes up front.
Thank you, Mrs. Haggly.
[sighs] As I was saying,
each year,
we honor the memory of General Pickens.
Yet few know the truth.
That it was
my great-great-great-grandpappy,
Colonel Barnabas B. Blossom,
who bankrolled
General Pickens' settlement of...
an Eden along the river of Sweetwater,
where maple trees grow taller
than the steeples
of Europe's grandest cathedrals,
which is why, every year,
I petition the mayor's office
to rename Pickens Day...
[school bell ringing]
[Haggly] Thank you for that, Cheryl.
Mr. Jones, we look forward
to your oral history report next week.
The students we transferred
to Riverdale High are fine,
but their parents are in my office,
every day,
wanting me to reopen Southside High.
Which is why we've been discussing
how our new neighborhood
could use something positive to focus on.
With your blessing,
we'd like to make Pickens Day bigger,
more of a celebratory event.
[Hiram] Sponsored by Lodge Industries.
And Andrews Construction co-sponsoring.
You mean you wanna turn Pickens Day
into a commercial for your SoDale project.
Like your open house.
[Veronica] Au contraire, Madam Mayor.
The open house was for investors.
But this event would be
for North-and Southsiders alike.
Two halves of a whole coming together...
To distract people with a party?
What if it backfires, things get violent?
What about the Serpents?
They've been quiet, but they're wildcards.
- They could cause trouble.
- [Hiram] We've thought of that.
We're offered to hire them
as event security.
Fred, you're on board with this?
[Fred] Well, FP told me the Serpents
are looking for work.
Figure we let them keep the peace.
You had your reasons
for closing down Southside High,
but this is an opportunity
to let the Southside know
- you're not turning your back on them.
- Hey, Dad.
- Hey, bud.
- Archie.
Sorry to interrupt.
- Mind if I join you guys?
- Actually, we're just finishing up.
Mm-hm.
- Thanks, Fred, for having us.
- Yeah.
Madam Mayor,
you'll let us know in the morning?
- Hey, Mr. Lodge.
- Excuse me, Archie.
Hey.
Oh, um...
I'd kiss you, but you're sweaty.
So, how long do you plan
on staying with us, Chic?
For as long as he wants.
I'm just trying to plan my life, Alice.
And since we're not getting any answers
about anything...
What would you like to know, Hal?
For starters,
Betty brought you here all bloody.
Why? What happened?
Dad.
You don't have to, Chic
The person who attacked me,
his name's Marcel.
He runs the hostel.
Sometimes he books clients for us.
The night you showed up, Betty,
I wasn't in the mood to work.
Marcel was trying
to convince me otherwise.
- So, what kind of clients?
- Hal.
No, I wanna know, too.
Betty.
All kinds.
Ranging from nice to, hell,
even nastier than Marcel.
I, uh, can go into specifics,
if you'd like.
I've also got a good collection
of scars I could show you.
I have scars, too.
Crescent moons on my palms.
From digging your nails in?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I used to do that, too.
Syrup.
[Alice clearing throat]
If and when the U.S. government
brings actions against Hiram Lodge
before any domestic court of law,
that agreement
ensures your father's immunity.
This is nuts. The Lodges were just
at my house planning a party.
- When was this? Who was there?
- Last night.
And it was Mr. and Mrs. Lodge, my dad,
the sheriff, Mayor McCoy, and...
That's it.
- Why weren't you a part of this?
- I was playing basketball.
Agent Adams,
what can we do to speed things up?
I just... I wanna get through this,
and back to my life, my normal life.
Do you have any relationship
with Hiram Lodge? Directly?
[scoffs]
- Nothing. He doesn't even like me.
- Then let's change that.
You have to establish trust,
get him to lower his guard around you.
The sooner you get access
to his inner circle,
the sooner we'll get what we need
to bring him in.
Then you can go back to playing
in the band with your pals and gals.
Well, he is very fetching
for someone who was living on skid row.
Yeah, he's a hottie who looks
incredibly familiar to me, by the way.
- Your adventures in the woods?
- Maybe if we were allowed
- to meet this hottie in person...
- [Betty] Chic is still acclimating.
And I'm trying to get him to trust me,
but my mom is treating him
like he's a 10-year-old,
and my dad's acting
like he's the devil's spawn.
Well, I have an amazing idea.
Bring The Omen to Pickens Day,
and we can all meet him.
Everyone's coming, right?
- No. Because the Serpents weren't invited.
- Serpents were specifically asked to come.
Yeah, to provide security.
Like we're all on the Snowpiercer train,
but the Serpents are
eating the cockroaches.
[Veronica] You don't have to work
if you don't want to.
[sighs] The damage, as they say,
has already been done.
- I'll talk to you guys later.
- Plans with Toni?
Uh, yeah. I'm interviewing her grandfather
for my oral history report.
Oldest living Serpent.
[Veronica] Archie, what is it?
I feel stupid even talking about this,
but... it's about your dad.
I get the feeling
he doesn't really like me.
What?
No, that's not...
That's not true.
Okay, maybe it's a little true,
but it's not anything you're doing,
per se. It's more that...
For starters, you don't speak Spanish.
I can drop French
and start taking Spanish.
- This is really bothering you, isn't it?
- To be honest, yeah.
Do you have any suggestions
on what I can do?
To endear yourself to Daddy?
Well... now that we're talking about it...
[Archie] What, your dad likes wrestling?
He was captain of Riverdale High's
wrestling team back in the day.
Says it changed his life.
Now that the season's starting back up,
it's like my mom and I
are background extras
in the movie Foxcatcher.
Wrestling? Really?
Lodge Industries
basically bankrolls the team.
He was just asking his old coach
if he could sit in on tryouts.
God, Ronnie, you know what's super weird?
I was just telling Reggie
how I was gonna take a break
from basketball this year.
It'd absolutely score you points
with my dad.
[Jughead]
Thanks again for meeting with me.
Toni told me that you're one
of the founding members of the Serpents.
Yes. The snake, the laws,
all based on Uktena tradition.
Who were the Uktena?
Uktena is a serpent,
a horned serpent or water serpent.
Before there was Riverdale,
all this land belonged to the Uktena.
How'd the Uktena evolve into Serpents?
[laughing]
The Uktena, we didn't evolve.
We were all slaughtered.
When my grandpa was a baby,
there was a raid.
And it was led by your hero there,
General Pickens,
in a battle, if you wanna call it that.
Only lasted for 12 minutes.
But the slaughter was total and savage.
The General Pickens?
Whose statue stands proudly
in Pickens Park?
Yes. And every year the Northside honors
this man who massacred children.
When my grandpa died,
we formed the Serpents as a way
to keep the family together.
- How do people not know about this?
- Ah, some do, but...
It's called the whitewashing of history,
Jones.
What, did you think Jason Blossom
was the first person
to be murdered in Riverdale?
You know I'm down to help,
but why can't it just be the two of us
singing a duet at Pickens Day?
I mean, it could be,
but the Pussycats are a brand.
Why let it sit fallow?
Josie. Veronica. What's this all about?
We are bringing back the Pussycats
to play Pickens Day.
Whose idea was that?
Uh, it was Veronica's.
Weren't we focusing on your solo career?
We could bill it as a special event,
one night only.
I was talking to my daughter.
In fact, why don't we continue
this conversation later
when it's just us two?
[cell phone buzzing]
- Hey, Kev, what's up?
- Are you somewhere where you can talk?
Yeah, why?
I just remembered where I know Chic from.
He's a video gigolo,
a webcam boy, a cyber trick.
[inaudible dialogue]
== Synced & corrected by MaxPayne ==
Mom.
A really weird thing happened
when I was at Josie's last night.
Mayor McCoy was acting
like I was a bad seed,
out to corrupt her daughter.
I don't believe Sierra is comfortable
with how we let you become involved
in the business.
- Why does she even care?
- She's afraid you're gonna tell Josie.
- I'd never...
- Of course not, mija.
And I am not making excuses for Sierra.
In fact, should her coldness persist...
I'll happily have a conversation with her.
[Hiram] Thought basketball was your sport.
- I'm branching out.
- Ah.
- What are you doing here, Mr. Lodge?
- Just, uh, checking out the team.
- I wrestled in high school.
- Really?
- No, I didn't know that.
- What weight class you in?
One seventy-five,
I'm trying to get down to 170.
Hey, Andrews. It's a good thing
you're not in my weight class.
I'd wreck you, Gingerbread Man.
[whistle blowing]
Let's bring it in.
Firstly, I wanna thank a gentleman
who's really showing his support
for the team this year.
He wrestled for me my first year as coach.
That is Hiram "The Ram" Lodge.
Guys, let's show him some appreciation.
[all applauding]
Thank you.
Listen up.
Not everyone will make the team this year.
There'll be cuts every day, boys,
so, make each match count.
All right. Pair off.
Up-and-downs.
Let's go.
You do know wrestling's
not like football or basketball, right?
I went up against Moose
in the Oklahoma Drill, Kev. I'm good.
[sighs]
[whistle blowing]
[grunting]
[Keller] Thattaboy.
Okay, reset.
Again.
[whistle blowing]
[panting]
[Kevin] It felt so good, Betty.
It's like, "Archie, you have the physique
of a 1970s porn star,
- but that doesn't mean you can wrestle."
- Speaking of porn stars...
Did you get lost
down a webcam rabbit hole?
It's fascinating.
I brought Chic home to help my mom
without knowing who he was,
and now to find out
he's actually multiple people,
performing online...
How do I broach that with him?
Do I broach that with him?
[knocking on door]
Hey. Am I interrupting?
- Yeah, kind of...
- No.
I wanted to run stuff by you.
I can come back.
No, no, no, it's fine.
Bye.
By the way, I'm really digging
Kevin's new gossip column.
Readers love it.
And I needed to fill the extra space
when you...
I'm actually working on a story right now.
Here.
When I interviewed Toni's grandfather,
he had some pretty intense things to say
about General Pickens.
But I did some follow-up research.
General Pickens was hired
by Barnabas B. Blossom
to remove the Uktena tribe by force.
Betty, he killed 400 innocent men,
women, and children.
My God, that's horrible.
And adding salt to the wound,
the last remnants of the tribe,
the Serpents,
are being squeezed out of existence.
Toni's grandfather lives
in a trailer the size of a broom closet.
Hiram Lodge is honoring this murderer,
instead of trying to make amends.
I think it's a story we need to tell.
Will you try to get a quote from Hiram?
[Veronica] Kevin told me what happened.
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
Bruised ego, more than anything.
But Kevin's gonna work with me,
- get me up to speed.
- Great.
But should you
not be a natural-born wrestler,
I thought of another way
you might curry my father's favor.
Though Pickens Day is taking a backseat
to his wrestling obsession,
he will be there,
and I suspect he'd be tickled
to see you sing with me and Josie.
Chic. Hey.
- He threw out my stuff.
- What? Who did? What stuff?
Marcel, my landlord, the guy you maced?
He got rid of everything.
Everything I need to survive.
- My laptop, my camera...
- You went back there? And talked to him?
- After what he was doing to you?
- My entire life was at that hostel.
Like my mom said,
you can stay here as long you want.
- You don't think this is long-term.
- I don't know. Maybe.
Wow. Wow.
If you believe that,
you're even crazier than I thought.
[phone ringing]
- This is Hiram.
- [Jughead over phone] Hi, Mr. Lodge?
Yeah, this is Jughead Jones,
I'm writing an article
about how General Pickens
massacred the Uktena tribe
and stole the land you're building on.
[sighs]
[door opens]
I'm sorry he sold all your stuff.
[sighs]
♪ Can you hear me? ♪
♪ Am I drowned out in the crowd? ♪
- ♪ Are you...? ♪
- [knocking on door]
Hey. What are you guys doing in here?
We're just working
on some Pickens Day songs.
Archie's agreed to help.
Yeah, we can take it to the living room,
- Mr. Lodge...
- No. No.
Not at all.
I have to say,
the thought of you two being
in here alone used to upset me deeply.
After seeing your performance today,
Archie, for some reason I'm less worried.
- Daddy, be nice.
- Not everyone can wrestle.
- It takes a certain kind of man...
- Excuse me, "man"?
My point is there's no shame,
Archie, in admitting defeat.
And accepting the fact that you're more
suited to singing with the Pussycats.
Daddy,
Archie may not be a star wrestler yet,
but he's an incredible musician.
And bonus for me,
incredibly sexy when he sings.
Thanks, babe.
Ah.
Maybe I shouldn't be spreading myself
too thin these days.
Honestly?
Yeah, I should get home,
practice some moves Kevin showed me.
But I'll see you at tryouts tomorrow,
I hope?
Yeah.
Do you know who used to sit there?
- Dad.
- Our daughter, Polly.
You sit in her chair,
you sleep in her bed.
You're filling a void.
That's the reason you're here.
The only reason.
It's okay, it doesn't bother me.
Everyone needs something.
And I don't expect to stay here for free.
I never have.
[whistle blowing]
[Kleats]
We're focusing on fundamentals today.
Starting with the fireman's carry.
And since it was his signature move,
back in the day,
I've asked Hiram Lodge here
to demonstrate.
Ram, will you do us the honor?
All right, then. I need a volunteer.
Archie Andrews.
Come on.
- What are you waiting for?
- Mr. Lodge?
Come at me. Come on.
This is a simple but effective move
when your opponent gets cocky.
Dominating your rival,
demoralizing him...
is the key if you want to win.
[grunting]
Get the message. I always win.
[Toni] "General Pickens was a murderer,
and ripples from his gruesome acts
continue to be felt today.
Descendants of the victims
are still being displaced.
So, I challenge the Northside,
instead of honoring men
like General Pickens and Hiram Lodge,
hold them accountable.
Reparations must be paid
to men like Thomas Topaz,
who are too old and beaten down
to fight back for themselves"?
This town is messed up,
and it needs to own up to its history.
My grandfather
isn't some broken-down victim. Okay?
Or some prop for your insane vendetta
against the Northside.
- No, of course not.
- Look.
I get it.
You hate the Northside.
You hate that instead of inviting you
to a party, they asked you to work it.
It triggers your rage about being born
on the wrong side of the tracks. But this?
This wasn't your story to tell.
[sighs]
[McCoy] I can't cancel Pickens Day,
but I don't want you performing at it.
With the town riled up over this article?
What if there's a riot?
No one's rioting, Mom,
and I promised Veronica.
Okay, well, I'm sorry,
you can tell her that the Pussycats
aren't hers to order around.
Why is Veronica triggering you
all of a sudden?
Baby,
let me tell you something about Veronica.
And her parents.
And the way they do business.
And the way they use their daughter
to do their business.
♪ Nightshades on a warning ♪
♪ Give me strength or give me light ♪
♪ Give me anything
Even sympathy ♪
♪ There's a cha... ♪
- You're late.
- I'm out.
I'm not performing at Pickens Day.
- Wait, what?
- It's just...
I don't like being manipulated by a Lodge.
What?
Josie, is your mom making you do this?
My mom?
Whatever she
and your parents have going on,
that's between them.
She doesn't want me to be a part of it.
My mom says she may have
to do what your parents want,
- but I don't have to do what you want.
- What? Josie...
Cameras aren't here, Jackie O.
And what about Jughead's article?
What about it, Cheryl?
It says
that Great-great-great-grandpappy Blossom
hired General Pickens
to steal land from the Uktena.
Well, how do you think we got started
in the maple syrup business? Help me up.
But then that means
our family is partly responsible
for killing literally hundreds of people.
For what? A bunch of maple trees?
It wasn't just trees.
Dark, fertile earth.
A mighty river. Back in those early days,
we had a hand in everything.
Building the rail roads,
operating the saloons.
And, yes, even a brothel.
The old ways die hard, it seems.
- [Kevin] You're definitely getting better.
- I appreciate the help, Kevin.
- You're a legend.
- Anytime. Can I ask something?
Why wrestling?
Why now?
I mean, trying to impress Mr. Lodge?
To be honest, it didn't start there.
But now... yeah, it's like there's nothing
I can do to earn his respect.
And the more he looks down on me,
the more I wanna show him that he's wrong.
Yeah. It's personal now.
- [Chic] Why'd you buy me that laptop?
- Oh, um...
I didn't. It's just an old computer I had
from the Register.
Why'd you come get me?
You're my brother.
And my mom was depressed...
No. Sorry, everything is a transaction.
No one, not even you, is that nice.
So, why do you care, Betty?
What do you want?
And careful, I'll know if you're lying.
To figure out why I am the way that I am.
There's a darkness in me
that I don't understand.
That scares me.
And I thought that maybe,
if you had it, too, which I think you do,
you'd be able to help me make sense of it.
I know about the webcamming.
That's why I got you the computer.
So, if you ever wanna talk about that,
or compare scars...
No, thanks, I'll pass.
[Archie] I told the doorman I was here
to see Veronica.
And I'll have speak to Andre about that.
What is it, Archie?
Why don't you like me, Mr. Lodge?
Why? What did I ever do to you?
You really asking that?
- You really don't know?
- Yeah, I am, and no, I don't.
Your father slept with another man's wife.
And why shouldn't I assume
you have the same weak character?
I'm not my dad, Mr. Lodge. I would never...
Maybe that's true,
but still, you're not good enough
for my daughter in any respect.
You're not worthy.
You'll never be able to take care of her.
I did while you were in prison.
Excuse me?
When she and Mrs. Lodge
moved to Riverdale,
I was there for your daughter.
You couldn't be.
You would say that to me?
In my house?
[Veronica]
What the hell is going on in here?
- Veronica, ahem...
- Hey, we were just...
Having some juvenile
chest-thumping contest?
No. Not at all.
I just asked Archie to come over
and plan some one-on-one training.
Really? That why it looks like
you're about to kill each other?
[cell phone buzzing]
- Hello?
- [Hiram] Meet me outside in five minutes.
Mr. Lodge?
What time is it?
[call disconnects]
[pop music playing]
[Hiram] Thank you.
You know why I love wrestling?
Because when it's two men on the mat,
it doesn't matter who you are.
Or where you come from.
Or how strong you are.
It's about sheer will.
And knowing your opponent.
Maybe even better than he knows himself.
Which is why, Archie...
you will never win.
- What are you talking about?
- Veronica...
has a lot on her plate.
And I don't want her worrying about us.
So, after this morning,
we can say that I helped you.
And that we went for a jog
and we broke bread together.
And I will tolerate you...
- until this phase runs its course.
- Runs its course?
You're not the first boy
to turn her head.
You see, boyfriends,
they come and they go.
But fathers...
fathers are forever.
[Hermione] You're not hungry, mija?
Is it Archie and your dad?
No, it's Josie.
We got into a fight
and she dropped out of Pickens Day.
I see.
This is Sierra's doing, I assume?
That's it.
- I'm taking care of this.
- No, Mom. It's like you said.
Our family works differently
from other families.
If Josie and Mayor McCoy
don't like how we do business,
that's on them.
But the show must go on.
I was angry,
because the Southside is our home.
I'm sick of watching it get dismantled,
piece by piece, in front of our eyes.
They take our drive-in,
then take our school.
- I thought you were apologizing.
- I am.
I shouldn't have used your story
or what happened to the Uktena
against the Northside.
I had no right...
I had no right.
I'm sorry.
Whatever your reasons were...
you opened an old wound.
Now something has to be done to heal it.
Do you have something in mind, Grandpa?
[rock music playing on headphones]
What are you doing here?
Daddy invited me.
He said it was your last day of tryouts
and I should come.
He says you guys had a good talk.
Anyway, not that you need it,
but good luck.
I'll be in the stands, cheering you on.
[whistle blowing]
Gather around, boys.
We're gonna change things up a bit.
First up on the mat is Andrews,
who is going up against Clayton.
Wait, coach, isn't Chuck
in a higher weight class than me?
Damn, Andrews.
You sound like my little sister.
Come on, time for Thunderdome.
[Kleats] Enough chatter. Center. Now.
[Jaden Smith's "Watch Me" playing]
[whistle blowing]
♪ Watch me, do this
Watch me, watch me ♪
Can't find me up, up and away ♪
♪ I give a f*** 'bout your wave
My n****, I surf every day ♪
♪ Drownin' my soul in the basement
I ain't got much in the bank ♪
♪ I got a lot I could say ♪
♪ Tied up with goddesses, hey
I hope you forgive my mistakes ♪
Shoot.
♪ I try to heal the gods with a band-aid ♪
♪ And in time of need
You call your enemies ♪
♪ That's what they yell
When we come around ♪
That's right, Archie. Get him.
♪ How big is your army, a hundred thou? ♪
♪ If you want the rain
Then we comin' down ♪
♪ Watch me, watch me
Watch me, do this ♪
♪ It's always been more than the music ♪
♪ You riding waves
On the back of my cruise ship ♪
♪ Watch me ♪
[Kleats] One.
Two.
Three.
Whoo!
Eat up. Can't have an empty stomach
for Pickens Day.
Especially since
it's our first family outing.
Actually, I'm, uh, staying behind.
I have a few odd jobs
to catch up on around the house.
Fine, Hal. I won't beg.
Salad.
[marching band music playing]
[chattering]
Sierra. I'm so glad you made it.
Josie,
sorry you aren't singing with us today.
After that article came out,
I forbade her to, Hermione. I was worried.
Can't be too careful
when it comes to our children.
That was a surprise, Archie.
Your victory over Clayton.
Thank you, sir.
Are we done, Mr. Lodge?
Come by The Pembrooke tonight.
We should talk about some things.
I'll be there, sir.
[Alice] Have you ever had
a maple snow cone?
I have not. Is it delicious?
Oh, Chic.
Betty, I'm so happy.
Mom, Mom, Mom.
- Alice.
- I thought you said you weren't coming.
Do you know what you've let
into our house?
- In the room right next to Betty's?
- Lower your voice.
What are you talking about?
I went on your computer, Chic.
I saw what you're doing online
with your clients.
Dad, stop.
Stop snooping, and stop harassing him.
I don't wanna hear it from you.
You bring home this... stranger,
- and move him into Polly's bedroom?
- It's not Polly's room anymore, Hal.
It's Chic's.
He has to go, Alice,
and you know damn well why.
Hal, I swear,
I threw you out once, I'll do it again.
[microphone feedback]
Hello, Riverdale. Ahem.
Happy Pickens Day.
On behalf of Lodge Industries
and Andrews Construction,
we are thrilled to kick things off
with a new twist on an old favorite.
So, Veronica and the Pussycats.
[crowd cheering]
♪ Nightshades on a warning ♪
♪ Give me strength or give me light ♪
♪ Give me anything
Even sympathy ♪
♪ There's a chance you could be right ♪
♪ If I listen close
I can hear them singers ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Voices in your body coming through
On the radio ♪
♪ The Union of the Snake ♪
♪ Is on the climb ♪
♪ Moving up, it's gonna race
It's gonna break ♪
♪ Through the borderline ♪
♪ The Union of the Snake ♪
♪ Is on the climb ♪
♪ Moving up, it's gonna race
It's gonna break ♪
♪ Through the borderline ♪
Toni?
Jughead? What the hell is going on?
We're here representing the dead
and the silenced.
Pickens Day is a lie.
General Pickens slaughtered
the Uktena tribe,
my grandfather's family,
and this land,
the land that we're standing on,
that will soon give way
to a new Southside,
was stolen from them.
And we can't bring them back.
But we can and we must honor them.
Hey, folks, hi. Uh...
I think we can all be proud
to live in a Riverdale
where young people stand up for justice.
Where a young woman can defend the honor
and legacy of her grandfather.
And where we can celebrate
the living legacy of the Uktena,
who contribute to the rich tapestry
that is Riverdale,
that is the Southside,
and that will be SoDale.
So, let's hear a round of applause
for that, am I right?
That's right. What do you say, people?
No.
How about we get you a proper dessert,
Hal?
It looks like you could use
some company and...
I've got nowhere I need to be.
[chuckles]
[Chic] Can I come in?
Sure.
Betty, I have a confession to make.
The first night I was here,
I came into your room while you slept.
- What?
- I kept waking up that night.
Trying to understand, why would this girl
go back to that place for me?
But I think maybe I understand now.
You're alone here.
We'll start with why I webcam.
One of the reasons is to make money.
The other reason is to escape.
Pretend to be someone else.
Yes, but...
more than that.
It's a way of getting away
from the darkness I feel inside me, too.
Can you show me how to do that?
[Jughead] And so,
with the stroke of a few keys,
the dark education
of Betty Cooper had begun.
And also, perhaps,
the criminal apprenticeship
of Archie Andrews.
Let's start with a blank slate, Archie.
Where do you see yourself in five years?
College. Hopefully on some type
of athletic scholarship.
To study music?
No, that was the old me.
Now I'm thinking more like... business.
Maybe one day I can buy back
Andrews Construction from you.
Archie, as long as you're dating Veronica,
I'm going to demand the best from you.
And that requires learning from the best.
Like to start your business tutelage
under my shepherding?
[cell phone buzzing]
Sorry about that.
Like an internship?
[Jughead] That night, plans would be made,
alliances would be formed,
and a horrifying act of desecration
would be committed.
Must've happened late last night
or early this morning.
Well, Hiram, Hermione, it's your show now.
How would you like this handled?
Swiftly, and with extreme prejudice.
We all know
who the most likely suspects are.
I mean, you tell me.
Isn't it something the Serpents would do?
[Jughead] Ensuring that the town's
civil war would go from a possibility
to an inevitability.