- [narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
- [gunshot]
[Alice] He calls himself the Black Hood.
[Pop] It's like the angel of death
had come to Riverdale.
A family of four was murdered.
[Veronica] There was a third child.
You know who killed your family?
A preacher passing through town.
A group of men killed him.
Justice had been served.
I know about the Snake Charmer.
If you cause a stink, I will make sure
that video goes straight to the sheriff.
I love you, Ronnie.
Archie, whatever issues I have,
I can't let myself go there with you.
How many times
are we gonna push each other away?
[Christmas music playing over speakers]
♪ This Christmas has been so hard ♪
[Jughead] Used to be, in ye olden days,
every December, a lord of misrule presided
over the winter holidays,
called, back then, the Feast of Fools.
What do you say, Pop? Is it okay?
The best tree yet.
Thanks, Archie. Thanks, Fred.
Thank you, for letting us set up shop
in front of the diner.
You guys gonna stay in town for break?
Yeah. We were gonna visit my mom,
but she booked a single's cruise, so...
- How are you and Veronica?
- We've been better.
If it's any consolation, Betty and I
haven't been in the greatest place.
Jughead, you want a Christmas tree?
You and your dad, on the house?
It would have to be a small one, Mr. A.
So, I'll see you
at Kevin's Secret Santa thing?
Yeah, that sounds like a great idea.
[both laughing]
So, Christmas was happening.
Even though this year's lord of misrule
was none other than the Black Hood.
Wake up, it's time.
- Polly? What? Who's here?
- He's here. He's waiting for us.
You know who. Come on.
[indistinct chatter]
- [Alice] Merry Christmas.
- [Hal] Hey, Merry Christmas.
- Betty.
- Betty, Merry Christmas!
- [Alice] Okay.
- [Hal] All right, honey,
I hope you like it.
- Santa?
- [Hal] Tear it open.
[Betty panting]
[gasps, then breathing heavily]
♪ O come, all ye faithful ♪
- Where's Jason's stocking?
- [Penelope] I couldn't find it.
And anyway, there's nothing to put in it.
And what, pray tell, is this?
It's going to be a hard-candy Christmas
this year, Cheryl.
Time to face facts. We have no money.
Dad, what is that?
That a letter from the Black Hood?
No, it's worse.
Riverdale General. My hospital bill.
How much is it for?
- Eighty-six thousand.
- Dollars?
That can't be right, can it?
Or doesn't your insurance...?
They probably made a mistake.
I'll call them tomorrow.
Kevin's Secret Santa had
a strict $20 limit, V.
Kevin needs to relax. Also,
these aren't just for Secret Santa, obvi.
I got an Hermès scarf for my mom,
a leather passport case for my dad
now that he can travel again,
and a little something for my best girl.
And... a bauble for Archie.
- You're getting back together?
- It was purchased pre-breakup.
Haven't you heard? We're still friends.
Oh, yeah. Isn't everyone?
[sighs]
I was thinking about our Penny problem.
My problem, not ours.
I'm the one that she has
on camera delivering drugs.
How I deal with Peabody is not
your concern. I'm handling it.
By pimping the Serpents out
as drug runners?
Boy...
- Toss them in the corner.
- Hey, what's in the bags, Tall Boy?
Hey, what did I just say?
Mind your damn business. Get to school.
Veronica, it's your turn.
Hmm.
Oh, a gift certificate
for a couple's massage.
- Thanks, Josie.
- You can go with Betty.
- Or your mom.
- I can go with your mom.
Dear God, can we please get
this torture over with?
Betty, you're next, and mercifully last.
I think I know who picked my name
based on these wrapping skills. [chuckles]
Archie.
[Archie] My dad and I were cleaning out
the garage, and I found it.
- [Veronica] Swiss Family Robinson?
- [chuckles]
Yeah, it's this old read-along record
we used to listen to
when we were, like, 5. Oh, my God.
- I love it, Arch. Thank you.
- Hey, Merry Christmas.
- [Reggie] Moose.
- Hi.
- Hi, Midge.
- What's up?
- How are you?
- [Betty] Why are you rushing off?
Look, Betty, I don't wanna be that guy.
But I see Moose,
all I think about is the Black Hood
and the pain he's caused to the people
that I care about, including you.
I know. And the fact that he's still
out there is giving me anxiety nightmares.
Making me paranoid. It's like
everywhere I look, all I see is...
What? All you see is what?
Excuse me, who are you?
You mean, my name?
Uh, where's Mr. Svenson?
No idea. He's been out a few days.
They just called me in.
You and Veronica confronted Mr. Svenson
- about his connection to the Black Hood.
- And now he's not here.
- What if something happened to him?
- We found out Mr. Svenson's secret.
What if we led the Black Hood to him?
What if we got him killed?
Subtitles by explosiveskull
[Doris] Mr. Svenson?
He's been out all week with a cold.
Oh, sounded terrible on the phone.
So, I dropped off some chicken soup
at his house a few days back.
- You saw him?
- I left it at his door.
But between us, he often gets this way
during the holidays, you know? Depressed.
No family.
- Thank you.
- [school bell ringing]
Hey, I... stayed behind, 'cause...
Merry Christmas.
Thank you.
Look, I'm sorry.
For how it all went down between us.
As Serpents, my dad and I specifically
are in a precarious place.
I... just don't want you
in those crosshairs.
That's not your decision to make, Jughead.
Even if you think it's to protect me,
it's my choice what I risk and for whom.
I know.
I should go. Check in on my dad.
Jug.
I got you something, too.
[grunts]
[school bell ringing]
Archie.
- I got you a little something.
- Thanks.
I didn't realize...
Oh, no, no, it's all good. Just open it.
- Ronnie, this is...
- Turn it over.
I got it before...
I don't want things
to be forced between us.
- [exhales]
- What?
No, did I make it worse? I just wanted you
to know that I still care about...
No, you didn't.
Things at home aren't great right now.
It's my dad.
Anything I can do to help?
Come on, we're still friends.
He just... He got his hospital bill,
and he owes... $86,000, Ronnie,
and it's like we're
selling Christmas trees
just for extra money
so we can keep our heads above water.
Oh, my God, Archie.
I wanna help, but...
- I wanna hug you.
- That's okay.
I shouldn't have said anything.
The watch is great, Ronnie.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
[Jughead] What is all this?
It's Serpent tradition.
Every year, we give back to the Southside.
Toys for Tots, Meals on Wheels,
kids and old folks living alone.
The Hells Angels do it.
I'm always down for charitable works.
Hey, have you seen my dad?
[FP] Why aren't you in school?
Uh, it's a half-day before break.
Well, in that case, you can hold down
the fort here, Jug.
Or I could come with you guys.
Nice try. The answer's no.
- We do need another set of hands.
- There you go. Let me pull my weight.
Dad.
I don't know what
the Snake Charmer has you doing...
Sweet Pea, you're with us.
[cell phone ringing]
- Hey, Betty, what's up?
- Hey, I can't let this Svenson thing go.
I think we should stop by his house
and check up on him.
Yeah, I agree. Let me just tell my dad,
then we'll go.
- Give me ten.
- Okay.
Team Paul Bunyan.
I'd like to purchase your finest tree.
Actually, Cheryl, I was just about to take
a break, but Vic here can help you. Vic.
What can I get you?
We got some nice spruces.
[Betty] There's the chicken soup.
[knocking on door]
Mr. Svenson!
Can I help you?
Jughead Jones?
Maybe.
I'm Jack Walsh, your dad's parole officer.
He's not home.
Doesn't need to be.
Do you mind if I come in?
Like I have a choice.
Hiram, was that a Spiffany's bag
I saw come into the lobby earlier today?
Looked about the right size
for a Glamergé egg.
That depends.
Have you been naughty or nice?
[Hermione laughing]
[Hiram] Don't worry, mija.
Santa has your list, too.
And please don't go snooping
for the gifts this year. He hates that.
Santa can rip up my list for all I care.
I mean, look at us,
throwing money away on bejeweled eggs
like we're a family of Russian oligarchs
when there are people in this town who
can't even pay their own medical bills.
Since when are you a communist?
Since Archie told me that he and his dad
are drowning in Fred's medical bills
to the tune of $86,000,
which is why I was thinking...
- Absolutely not.
- That's a lot of money.
The Lodge charitable trust has made
its donations for the fiscal year.
Fred Andrews will have
to tighten his belt.
Said Ebenezer Scrooge.
Fred's selling Christmas trees
for extra cash.
I mean, that's the kind of man...
The kind of father he is.
You know...
I believe I have some work
to finish in the study.
[humming]
[Penelope] Cheryl Marjorie Blossom,
what have you done?
Isn't it obvious, Mother?
I've saved Christmas.
Look how happy Nana Rose is.
You spoiled, wretched little brat.
How do you expect to pay for all this?
Oh.
I was thinking maybe you could go
to Mr. Lodge for a job.
Of course, he'd probably ask what skills
you have, and you'd be forced to admit
that the only skill you have is being
a terrible mother.
I guess you're gonna have
to get creative in the new year.
[sighs]
You should've drowned them at birth,
like a basket of kittens.
Mom? Dad?
Betty.
- Hey.
How are you?
Fine, I just iced
some ginger bread cookies.
Polly's favorite.
Just in case there's a Christmas miracle
and she comes home.
Oh, by the way, there was a gift
for you on the steps.
Your secret Santa.
I took it up to your room.
Secret Santa?
[gasps]
"Enclosed is a finger that belongs
to the sinner Joseph Conway."
He's talking about Mr. Svenson.
"You have one final trespass to unearth.
Find the truth, reveal it to the town,
and you'll perhaps save his life."
He kidnapped Mr. Svenson, Arch.
And now he's mutilating him.
[cell phone buzzing]
Arch, Arch. Hey.
- [Svenson] Betty, please.
- Mr. Svenson, is that you?
[Black Hood] It is, Betty,
but his name's Joseph Conway.
He's lost a lot of blood.
Though it's nothing compared to the blood
on the hands of this town.
Exhume the past,
find where the primal sin was committed
and you'll find
the sinner Conway may be alive.
- And as always, don't...
- What?
You maniac. Don't tell Sheriff Keller?
[line beeps]
Archie, what sin? What can
Mr. Svenson possibly be guilty of?
Veronica and I talked to him.
His entire family was murdered
by some crazy preacher.
Maybe the people who adopted him
know something we don't.
Wait. Before he was adopted,
Mr. Svenson lived as Joseph Conway
at the Sisters of Quiet Mercy.
- Will they talk to us?
- They better.
["Here Comes Santa Claus" playing
over speakers]
♪ Right down Santa Claus lane ♪
♪ He's got a bag that's filled with toys
For boys and girls again ♪
♪ Hear those sleigh bells jingle jangle
What a beautiful sight ♪
♪ Jump in bed, cover up your head
Because Santa Claus comes tonight ♪
- ♪ Here comes Santa Claus ♪
♪ Right down Santa Claus lane ♪
♪ He doesn't care
If you're a rich or poor boy ♪
♪ He loves you just the same ♪
♪ Santa knows that we're God's children ♪
♪ That makes everything right ♪
Merry Christmas, Mom.
♪ 'Cause Santa Claus comes tonight ♪
Pop's?
- Did you open them?
- No, Dad.
Out of respect for you.
But your parole officer, Mr. Walsh,
he sure was curious.
- Walsh was here?
- Yeah. Don't worry. I got rid of him.
But he already has heard that the Serpents
are moving into narcos territory.
[FP] Ta-da.
Gift boxes?
- With drugs in them?
- No, with gifts in them,
for you, your mom, Jellybean.
Christmas Day, I thought we'd take a ride
to Toledo and deliver them in person.
Dad, this isn't gonna work.
Today, it's gifts, tomorrow, it's drugs,
or weapons, or God knows what.
- How long is this gonna go on...?
- As long as Penny wants.
If her favors keep getting bigger,
which you know that they will,
what happens when she asks
for more Serpents on this?
Then I'll bring more Serpents!
You know what? You're right, this isn't
gonna work, you and I living together.
So maybe you can go back to Fred's
or to Betty's.
- Betty? I split with Betty to...
- Then what do you want me to say?!
I just want you to let me help fix
this mess that I made.
Get this through your thick skull,
Jughead. We're trapped.
We got no leverage.
If that means I gotta be Penny's
dancing monkey for the time being,
then that's how it goes.
I'm gonna get some rest.
I have a long night ahead of me.
Yes, hello, I'm calling
to settle an account
for one of your patients, Fred Andrews.
Of course, I'm his business partner.
Uh-huh.
I'd like to pay the bill in full
and keep it anonymous,
an angel donation.
Yes, I'm aware of the amount.
My name?
Hermione Apollonia Lodge.
And it's a black American Excess card.
Number 29572300...
Penny Peabody has got
my dad dealing drugs.
I know this,
'cause she had me doing it before him.
Now she's roped in Tall Boy
and Sweet Pea.
Man, if you're pissed
because your old man tapped me...
No, Sweet Pea, I'm pissed
because I don't want the Serpents
to end up like the Ghoulies.
And I doubt
that any of you became Serpents
just to be at the beck and call
of a drug queenpin.
I know where this ends.
Death, jail.
Which is why
in the interest of self-preservation...
we have to take out Penny.
Snake Charmer's helped some of us.
Oh, yeah? What did she ask for
in return, Sweet Pea?
How many favors?
Now, if we don't stop Penny tonight...
she is going to get
every single one of us in on this.
I promise you. I promise you, Sweet Pea.
What I'm asking is,
are you willing to risk your necks
to save my dad's life?
- What is the first law?
- No Serpent stands alone.
I'm in.
Me too.
Let's do this.
Joseph Conway,
Joseph Svenson as you know him,
was a troubled youth.
- There was no saving him.
- Meaning, he was a sinner?
- No, he was a child, a victim.
- Did he suffer from survivor's guilt?
I've already said too much.
- [Betty] No.
- [Archie] Betty.
Sister Woodhouse,
when my sister escaped this dungeon,
she told me
all about the corporal punishment.
So, please help us with this,
or I will expose
the Sisters of Quiet Mercy
for the house of horrors
that it really is.
[Woodhouse]
After his family was massacred,
young Conway... Svenson identified
the man responsible.
Then a small group of Riverdale citizens
took matters into their own hands,
and, well, executed him.
It was only later when he was with us
that Joseph admitted that,
in his terror and shock,
he may have pointed a finger
of accusation...
At the wrong man.
Oh, my God.
Svenson's sin was sentencing
the wrong man to death.
Did Svenson...? Did Conway ever talk
about who carried out the execution?
They came here once to see Joseph.
It was a group of men and one woman.
I don't know their names.
And I can't remember
what they looked like.
Just that the woman had
the most striking hair.
White, save for a cherry-red stripe.
[Betty] Nana Rose Blossom?
[banging on door]
FP?
Well, you're early, old hoss.
Penny.
Ho, merry, ho.
[sighs] Jughead Jones.
Nice crowbar.
This? I brought it
in case I need to pry the door open.
Are you gonna give me a hand with this?
Your dad will be here in, like, what,
15, 20 minutes?
He probably won't be too happy
to see you, huh?
I wouldn't worry about that.
Neither of us are gonna be here.
[sighs]
Is this supposed to scare me?
I would not do this if I were you.
You are making a big mistake.
You are making...
Are you out of your mind?!
Hey, guys.
Finishing up some last-minute shopping?
We were, but then we got
the most fascinating call from our bank,
confirming a charge that was made
to my credit card, the amount of $86,000.
Oh. So that went through.
Great.
Yeah, I decided that you would cover
Fred's medical expenses.
I mean, if you can afford to buy Pop's
and then lie to my face about it.
So, how is it that we can now
suddenly afford an entire diner?
[Hiram] You wanted a more active role
in Lodge Industries
and we let you have it.
Then you break into my office and try
to use whatever you find as leverage.
Now, I admit, there's a lot
you don't know, and that's on purpose.
How can I be part of this family
if you keep hiding things from me?
Mija, you think you wanna know everything,
but you don't.
My name is on all of those documents
in your desk, Daddy.
Doesn't that mean
I have the right to know?
Yes, yes, it does, Veronica.
But that means the time
for being daddy's little girl is over.
It's time to work.
All of us in lockstep.
She deserves to know the truth, Hiram.
All right.
Follow me to the study.
[breathing heavily]
- Where am I?
- You're in Greendale.
Your new home.
But frankly, Penny,
I don't care where you set up shop.
But it's not gonna be in Riverdale,
and it's not gonna be with the Serpents.
You wanna deal drugs?
You wanna extort people?
That's your business.
But not on the Southside.
That belongs to us.
[laughing]
You stupid, cocky kid.
The Serpent law says
you can't hurt one of your own.
Oh, Penny, it's time you learn.
Grab her.
What are you doing?
Get off of me! Get off. Get off of me!
- That tattoo doesn't make you a Serpent.
- No, no. [screams]
No, no, no.
Cheryl, we need to see your grandmother.
Nana Rose seldom has visitors.
She'll be pleased. Entree.
[Betty] Nana Rose,
we have some questions for you
about something that happened
in Riverdale a long time ago.
A man killed his family,
and a group of people decided
- to take justice into their own hands.
- Oh, dear.
Here in Riverdale?
Yes, and you were part of that group,
weren't you?
- Is this a Christmas inquest?
- A man's life is at stake.
[Betty]
Were you with this group when they...?
When you killed this man for revenge?
Oh, no.
No girls allowed.
They told me to stay at home
while they took care of the bad man.
Nana Rose, this is so important.
Where did they hang the bad man?
Oh, they didn't hang him.
Oh, no. They gave him a proper burial.
Buried him alive.
Where? Where did they do that?
Ask your grandfather, Polly dear.
He was there.
My...? My grandfather?
I had a picture of them
smiling at the place.
Standing under the devil's hands.
Picture? What picture?
Cheryl?
I wonder if you might take me to my room.
I suddenly feel quite ill.
[Cheryl] Satisfied, you vultures?
Your reindeer games are over.
Now get the hell out.
Archie, my grandfather helped murder
an innocent man.
Betty, who even knows
if what she was saying is true?
That picture Nana Rose mentioned.
When Grandpa Louis died,
we packed up his house,
and we donated most of his stuff.
He had pictures.
We kept them and we organized them.
- Take a breath. Where are they?
- They're at my house.
- That's great.
- Archie,
my grandfather killed a man in cold blood.
An innocent man.
What if that's why he picked me?
The Black Hood.
That's why he's been calling me.
- Revenge for something I didn't do.
- Betty, listen.
This is the part... where we end this.
Where we save Mr. Svenson
and stop the Black Hood.
But I need you with me.
I can't do this alone.
Tomorrow, we're gonna wake up and
everything is gonna go back to how it was.
But right now, I need you with me.
- I need Betty Cooper.
- Arch.
Betty.
We have to hurry.
[Hermione] Well, Veronica.
Now you know.
You know everything.
So, mija, what do you think?
I'm in.
But I have ground rules.
Well...
one ground rule.
By all means.
- I refuse to do anything illegal.
- [Hermione] Well, that's fine.
Especially since we're not doing
anything illegal either.
Let me share two words to live by.
Plausible deniability.
Also... that charge I made
for Fred's medical bills?
- I want that to stick.
- It's gonna complicate matters.
- Fred is a proud man. He's not...
- We'll smooth that over.
And the truth is, we'll need Fred
for what comes next.
Fine. Assuming the Fred situation
can be finessed...
do we have a deal?
We do, Daddykins.
We have a deal.
- [Jughead] Hey, Dad.
- [FP] What's all this?
This is a celebratory dinner.
Penny didn't show up
for your pickup, did she?
No.
No, she didn't. Why?
Do you know something about that?
She's gone, Dad.
I rallied the younger Serpents.
We drove her out of Riverdale.
- I got my pound of flesh in the process.
- Are you nuts?!
- She'll be back. Better believe that.
- She won't!
I was very persuasive.
And even if she does,
we will take care of it.
You and me and the other Serpents.
In unity, there is strength.
That's the sixth law. While you were
in jail, I recited that. I lived by that.
You wanna take my jacket? You wanna
relegate me to Toys for Tots? Fine.
But I'm still a Serpent, Dad. And this?
This life you wanted to protect me from?
I'm proud of this.
I'm proud of who I am.
You can't take that away from me.
[Betty]
Nana Rose said it was a group of men.
I mean, there's one photo
that I kind of remember.
Dad said it was taken after Grandpa Louis
and some friends
planted some trees in Pickens' Park.
Wait.
Is this it?
[Archie] Look at the ground.
That's where they buried the preacher,
where Svenson could be maybe still alive.
Yeah, look at the branches.
- The devil's hand.
- That tree is in Pickens' Park.
We'll call Sheriff Keller on the way.
Come on.
[Betty] Look around. There.
Yeah.
Oh, my God, Archie.
[both panting]
Where's Mr. Svenson?
Why would the Black Hood bury
an empty coffin?
- What if it's a...?
- [gun cocks]
[Black Hood] Get in the coffin.
No. No way.
Get in the coffin or I shoot her
in the head. Right now!
Shut the coffin
and step out of the grave, Betty. Do it.
I'm sorry.
Pick up the shovel.
Fill in the grave.
[Betty sobbing]
Please don't make me.
[grunting]
We know what Mr. Svenson's sin is.
What he did.
That's the town's secret sin.
That's what you want revealed, right?
We can do that. I can do that.
Mr. Svenson, wherever he is,
he doesn't have to die.
Archie doesn't have...
[sirens wailing]
Archie.
- Where is he? Where'd he go?
- This way.
[Archie] Hey!
Stop!
Right down now!
Get down or I'll shoot you.
I swear to God, I'll do it.
You tried to kill my father.
And my friends.
You're gonna pay for your crimes.
You are not escaping. This ends tonight.
I said stop!
[gunshot]
[Keller] Archie, put the gun down.
- It's okay.
- Sheriff Keller.
[Keller] Stay back, Betty.
He's dead.
Who is he?
The town demanded blood for blood.
[Keller] Give me the gun.
[indistinct chatter]
["Silent Night" playing over speakers]
Your instinct about Svenson was right,
Ronnie. You thought he was the Black Hood.
We could've ended it at school,
where we confronted him.
I didn't see it,
I didn't see it in his eyes.
Forget his eyes.
I can't believe he cut off his own finger.
The finger of accusation.
[scoffs] So, we know who done it.
Why did he do it?
Mr. Svenson accused an innocent man
of murdering his family
and got the man killed.
Maybe in some backwards way,
he thought that targeting sinners
would balance the scales somehow.
I don't know.
No, no. It makes sense.
I mean, Svenson was always around,
lurking in the hallways.
He could've seen me and Miss Grundy
in the music room.
Yeah, he could have seen Moose
and Midge buying Jingle-Jangle.
Guys, this is starting to feel
like that last scene in Psycho.
The truth is...
I... have nothing, actually.
Except that he's in a body bag
and we aren't.
I think that's enough for tonight.
♪ Sleep in heavenly peace ♪
["God Rest Ye Merry Gentlemen" playing]
♪ Let nothing you dismay ♪
♪ Remember, Christ, our Savior ♪
♪ Was born on Christmas Day ♪
♪ To save us all from... ♪
Mother. Nana.
Is it time to open presents?
♪ O tidings of comfort and joy ♪
Santa?
[gasps]
Who's this one from?
Archie. He dropped it off yesterday.
[FP] Let me guess, that's from Betty.
It's a vintage Underwood.
It's the typewriter of champions.
You, uh... You maybe wanna swing by later?
Say thanks in person?
Oh, I'm...
I mean, I'll probably just call her
or text her.
♪ Now to the Lord sing praises ♪
♪ All you within this place ♪
♪ And with true love and brotherhood ♪
♪ Each other now embrace ♪
♪ This holy tide of Christmas ♪
[Archie] Wow, that sounds amazing, Mom.
You know, it's been quiet.
You too. I love you, too, Mom.
All right, here's Dad.
- [cell phone chimes]
- Hey there.
Merry Christmas, lady.
How are the Bahamas?
♪ Remember, Christ, our Savior ♪
Mmm.
♪ Was born on Christmas day ♪
Hey.
Merry Christmas.
Look up.
Mistletoe alert.
Hung by moi.
Now we have no choice but to kiss.
Archie.
You're so good.
It's like you're filled with it.
And I know that I need goodness
in my life.
I need you in my life.
In other words...
I love you, too, Archie Andrews.
[camera clicking]
[Jughead] And so another mystery
was wrapped up in a neat, tidy bow...
just in time for Christmas.
Throughout the Black Hood's reign
of terror,
Betty had stared
into the blackest of voids.
♪ God rest ye merry gentlemen ♪
The place where Joseph Conway's soul
had once perhaps existed.
And in that void,
she had seen a dark reflection.
A truth that could not be burned away.
♪ To save us all from Satan's pow'r
When we were gone astray ♪
A truth that whispered to her:
"This isn't over."
Subtitles by explosiveskull