- [narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
- I'm your Uncle Claudius.
Daddy never said anything
about having a brother.
The Lodges. Have I dreamt
of getting my revenge on them.
Now, Claudius, first things first,
Nana then Cheryl.
Effective immediately,
Southside High School is shut down.
- Okay, let's not overreact.
- [Jughead] Hiram is like Dracula.
He's snapping up properties
to expand his empire and feed.
Twilight Drive-In, Sunnyside Trailer Park,
Southside High,
- and Pop's Chock'lit Shoppe.
- Southside High will be turned into...
- A private, for-profit prison.
- We are leaving, and we are leaving now.
- Dad, I'll stay.
- This tradition has been in my family
going back generations.
Archie, we come first.
The only way I can get Chic
to open up...
But catfishing him?
[Betty] When you wouldn't submit
the DNA test,
I found your dental floss
and sent it to the lab.
You're not who you say you are,
Chic.
[Jughead] One sheet of paper.
That's all it took to confirm everything
Betty had feared.
That she'd let a dangerous stranger
into her house.
This is why you didn't want
the DNA test.
Because you knew the results.
You have no Blossom blood.
I don't. I'm not a Blossom.
I don't know them.
Blossom blood is Cooper blood, Chic.
My dad was a Blossom,
which means you would've tested positively
for Blossom DNA, but you didn't
because you're an imposter.
- Mom.
- [Alice] Betty, listen.
The truth is, Chic's DNA doesn't match...
because Hal isn't his father.
- But I am your mother, you understand me?
- Hang on. What?
- What? Then who is Chic's father?
- Chic's my son.
Whoever the father is
won't be a part of our lives.
There's no reason to open old wounds
that have healed many times over.
Come here.
Now, for our Register readers,
why would you, Hermione Lodge,
run for mayor of Riverdale?
Every year, our population decreases,
more and more businesses close.
We're at a deficit.
We need to change that
before it's too late.
That is why Lodge Industries has secured
a bid for a maximum security prison
on the Southside. Now, that means jobs,
economic growth, stability.
- It'll give Riverdale its future back.
- I have to ask.
You're building a prison
on the bones of a school.
Are you okay with that?
Losing a school is a tough pill
to swallow, but once our facility is up,
a quarter of our earnings
are gonna be funneled into education.
We are building a brand-new wing
at Riverdale High.
And, Veronica, are you going to follow
and run for student body president
- in the upcoming election?
- Maybe, if I don't have my hands full
campaigning for my mom.
I'm excited to show Riverdale
she's more than a housewife.
And speaking of housewives,
we have a very special guest,
Bravo's very own Andy Cohen.
Mr. Cohen, what brings you to Riverdale?
I'm here to endorse my great friend,
Hermione Lodge.
She's a very savvy businesswoman,
always three steps ahead
of everyone around her.
She's a fighter, too. She doesn't give up.
I'd love to have her in my corner.
[Veronica] Kevin just died
and went to Clubhouse heaven.
- Thank you for letting me invite him, Mom.
- Of course.
Any and all goodwill during this election
will go a long way.
And, Veronica...
this campaign isn't gonna be easy
since we had to lead
with your father's plans for the prison.
Certain people in town and in school
are gonna see us as the enemy.
After this endorsement,
let's keep our heads down,
- let the storm pass, understand?
- Color me a wallflower.
Dad, I know you think a prison
is a bad idea for Riverdale,
but Mr. and Mrs. Lodge
have thought this through.
A prison would rip the soul out
of the Southside.
So, I'm not gonna support that plan,
or Hiram and Hermione.
I'm severing ties with Lodge Industries
and SoDale. All of it. I'm done.
Just like that?
Will they let you walk away?
I'm not asking his permission.
They will, or they'll have
a hell of a fight on their hands.
I just loved your spin piece
in the paper, Olivia Pope.
Can we not, Jughead?
Did you know about Southside High closing?
Or the prison?
Of course not. That was all
her parents' doing. Right, V?
She didn't know, Jughead, okay?
So, back off.
Fine. I have to conserve my energy anyhow.
I'm going on a hunger strike
to protest Southside High closing
- and to get it reopened.
- [chuckles]
What?
Sorry, man, it's just...
You're always eating.
Good luck with that, but...
Hey, it's Jughead's prerogative
to protest peacefully,
- so, we're gonna support that, aren't we?
- Veronica?
Oh, hey, Ethel.
For your crimes against Riverdale,
everything your family has done
and continue to do, we find you guilty.
Your sentence is this.
[gasps]
The chilling thing is
Ethel went through the trouble
of bringing that milkshake here
from Pop's.
I mean, how mad is she?
My dad is responsible for the Muggs family
losing basically everything.
And he still hasn't made amends, so...
- [sighs] Ethel has a right to be upset.
- So do you.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'll manage.
I'm impressed.
I'd wanna rip Ethel's head off.
As my mom keeps saying,
"This is not the time for drama
and flying off the handle."
I just need...
to take deep breaths, keep smiling,
turn the other cheek.
Give Ethel a wide berth.
Veronica, I heard you got
a face full of dairy.
- I've got some nuts to top off that shake.
- Leave her alone, Reggie.
You do not wanna push me right now.
One question I gotta ask
as future student body president:
What are the odds
your dad's the first inmate
in that prison he's building?
Oh, man, that's heavy.
He'd be considered one of us.
Or is he building a female prison, too?
For your mom? Maybe I'll visit...
For your mom?
== Synced & corrected by MaxPayne ==
Who's there?
Oh, don't be ridiculous, Cheryl. No one
was trying to break into your room.
You're imagining things.
You're worse than Nana Rose.
- I know what I heard and saw.
- Claudius, we should talk about you
taking over Nana's stewardship
of the syrup business.
That factory's mine.
I'm not dead yet, you vultures.
Oh, Mother, now, come, come.
Let's not get too upset.
Have some more of Penelope's tea.
It's a special blend that she makes.
Are we feeling calmer this morning?
We are.
I'm drinking my High Point decaffeinated.
- So, you won't be punching a boy today?
- Again, I'm sorry, Mom.
Maybe if you'd offered Mr. Muggs
a job at the prison,
- all of this could've been avoided.
- Oh, no, no, no. No, mija.
We tell you what to do.
And right now, we're telling you, again,
keep your head in the sand.
Before it gets cut off.
We need you to be our good,
obedient little girl.
You can do that, right?
[Veronica] Friends, I have an exciting
announcement to make.
I'm running for student council president
- against Reggie "the Misogynist" Mantle.
- [groans] You've gotta be kidding me.
If yesterday's dramatic events
taught me anything,
it's that Veronica Lodge is not a victim,
nor will she ever allow herself to be one.
Your parents are taking over Riverdale,
you wanna take over school?
What is this, part of Mommy
and Daddy's evil bidding?
I get you're in a bad mood
because you haven't eaten...
Actually, my parents think
I should avoid the spotlight.
- Really?
- But I was born for elected office.
V, if you wanna be president,
you've got our vote.
- Yeah, Team Ronnie all the way.
- B, as the Thelma to my Louise,
I couldn't imagine doing this
with anyone else.
Will you be my running mate?
Of course, V.
- I'd be honored.
- Amaze.
B and V. Now, that's a team
you can believe in.
[DJ OLFO's "Rumbamba"
playing on speakers]
[music stops]
I don't think there's any way
you amateurs are gonna top that,
so practice is over, Vixens.
Inner circle Vixens, hang back.
You know who you are.
In honor of Toni joining our squad,
I think we should celebrate
with a slumber party at Thistlehouse.
Fancy dressing gowns are appreciated.
You've all seen The Beguiled.
Dinner at 8, parlor games to follow.
And there's nothing I can say
to change your mind?
Afraid not.
I just wanna get out of this thing.
As quickly, cleanly as I can. You go
about your business, I go about mine.
I understand.
And I will talk to Hiram.
- We need to get our lawyers involved.
- Yeah, yeah. I kind of figured that.
[Hiram] What can you tell me
about Jughead's hunger strike?
Yes, I heard about that.
Jughead loves a political crusade
almost as much as he does a burger.
Your friend seems to live in a
fantasy world of ideals and theoreticals.
What if Southside High were to reopen?
I live in the real world.
I see what needs to be done, and I do it.
I think you do, too, Archie.
I'm accelerating our timeline
on Southside High. I was wondering
if you could send Jughead a message.
- Yeah, whatever you need, Mr. Lodge, but...
- But why you?
I think it'll soften the blow
to hear it coming from a friend.
[Jughead] Hiram's tearing down
Southside High by the end of this week?
He's supposed to give the neighborhood
a six-weeks' notice.
Who'd he pay off? Can I have
another water, Pop? Thank you.
Jug, my dad got shot right here because
Riverdale was sliding off the deep end.
And if Mr. Lodge's plan
can shore things up
and help make Riverdale
more secure for our families,
I think that's a good thing.
Besides, why do you care so much?
You were only at Southside High
for four days.
You remember that I was raised
on the Southside, right?
My mom, my dad, Jellybean.
That neighborhood is the last
tangible piece I have of them.
Until your dad comes in
with his bulldozers.
My dad's actually against
this whole thing.
He's pulling out of his deal
with the Lodges.
And you're choosing Hiram's side over his.
We see things differently, okay?
And it makes me sick.
Like when you and your best friend
are two trains running on the same track
in opposite directions,
destined to collide?
[Sylvan Esso's "Die Young" playing]
♪ Now I gotta wait for you, honey ♪
Inner circle, Cousin Betty,
I didn't just bring you to Thistlehouse
for a girlish slumber party.
The truth is, I'm terrified
of being alone here.
There's a stranger in this house,
my Uncle Claudius.
He's mad. Ever since he blew in,
I feel like I'm in mortal peril.
I'm confused.
Is this real or are we playing?
All too real, Tee-Tee. I fear they're
plotting against me and Nana Rose.
Mumzie cultivates esoteric herbs
in the conservatory,
Tannis root, jimsonweed.
I'm afraid of being poisoned.
Cheryl, are you sure
you're not imagining things?
Well, if she is, Josie,
then maybe I am, too.
There's a stranger in my life as well.
Chic. With him lurking behind
every corner, my house feels...
Dangerous. Deadly.
I sympathize.
[Låpsley's "Falling Short" playing]
♪ And I know it sure ♪
♪ One month till February ♪
Full disclosure?
♪ And I know it sure ♪
I didn't want to invite
all the girls tonight.
But I knew my hideous mother
would never allow me to invite just you.
Which is...
what I craved.
♪ And it's times like these ♪
[crashing noise]
[screaming]
A fall like that should've killed her.
She's lucky.
Yes, that she is.
Poor thing loses her senses at nightfall.
It's classic sundowner's syndrome.
Cheryl, what is it?
- He's wearing my father's pajamas.
- [Toni] What?
My uncle.
Toni...
I think they pushed
my nana down the stairs.
And I think I'm next.
All this contract stuff with the Lodges?
Time to call in the big guns.
I wish you'd called me in earlier, Fred,
before you gave the Lodges
20 percent of Andrews Construction.
Mr. Lodge says he'll work this out.
He'll keep his word.
Yeah, son, your mother and I have known
the Lodges a lot longer than you have.
Meaning what, Dad?
Archie.
It's okay. I better get to school, anyway.
We still on for lunch, Mom?
Hands where I can see them.
[Betty Everett's "Shoop Shoop Song"
playing]
There you go.
- Now, remember, vote Lodge-Cooper.
- [scoffs]
Okay, who's next?
The cupcakes are
from Magnolia Bakery in New York,
but the kisses, however,
are locally sourced.
[stopwatch ticking]
- Uh, five-minute hydration break.
- [boy] Come on!
Ethel, wait.
Sexualizing the election?
It might get you the boys,
but forget about the girls.
Right now,
I'm only interested in one girl, you.
Look, I know it's long overdue,
but I wanna make reparations.
So, I'm working it out with my parents,
and tell your dad
to expect a great job offer
very, very soon.
This isn't a demolition notice.
It's a notice of extermination.
We've already said our goodbye
to Southside.
Today, it's Southside High,
tomorrow, it's the Wyrm.
Everything that makes
the Southside home...
is gonna disappear.
If we roll over now, it's all over.
- It's just a building, Jug.
- No, Toni, it's the soul of the Southside.
The Uktena fought and died
trying to protect that land.
Our parents fought
to keep it safe during the riots.
Now it's our turn.
It's our time.
This is our fight.
So, who's with me?
Who's ready to go to war?
Archie, I really hate to see you
and your father fighting.
We're not, Mom.
And look, you and Veronica,
it's your first real relationship.
I just wanna make sure
that you're not being...
- led astray.
- By Ronnie?
To align yourself with her family
against your better judgments.
It's not like that.
Veronica is an amazing person.
I'm sure she is.
But I guess I'm just saying...
so is your dad.
- [Kevin] Just the milk is.
- [Chic] The best you can get.
- [Kevin] Can't get anymore more milky.
- [Chic laughs]
[Kevin] So, good milk.
It is.
[Betty] Uh...
- What the hell is going on here?
- Chic invited me over.
Cookie?
No thanks.
How do you guys even know each other?
It's a funny story. Kevin and I
have been continuing our online chats.
Imagine my surprise
when he finally told me
it all started as a catfishing scheme
you cooked up.
- Kev, you sold me out?
- I felt bad.
Okay, you need to leave.
I need to talk to my brother alone.
- Betty, you're kicking me out right now?
- Mm-hm.
It's okay, Kev. I'll catch you later.
Do not mess with my friends.
Mess with?
What do you think I'm doing here, Betty?
Clearly, there's something you want,
some void you're looking to fill.
Like brother, like sister, right?
We share the same darkness.
Isn't that what you said?
Yeah, I guess I was wrong.
You know nothing about my darkness.
But you will.
Josie, look, I know things haven't been
smooth sailing between us.
Are we even on speaking terms? I mean,
you did steal the Pussycats from me.
Borrowed them, after you dumped them.
What do you want?
A celebrity endorsement for my campaign.
Yours.
And before you say no, Andy Cohen
is a very old,
very good friend of the family.
My ears are perked, because I never miss
an episode of Watch What Happens: Live.
- How would you like to be on it?
- What?
- As a special guest?
- If you can make that happen...
- consider yourself endorsed.
- Amazing.
My point is, Hermione, some may read
this document as exploitative.
- Come on, now, Mary. Now, that's not fair.
- Fair would be an immediate
and compensated release from the contract.
How does that sound?
- Oh, I'm sorry. That keeps buzzing.
- [cell phone buzzing]
Hiram here.
They're doing what?
[cell phone buzzing]
Mr. Lodge?
What?
Yeah, don't worry. I'm on it.
Well, well, well, cavalry's finally here.
Guess that means we got Hiram's attention.
Are you nuts?
Chaining yourself to this place?
They're gonna tear it down in two days.
Not unless Hiram wants the blood
of eight young Serpents on his hands.
We're not going anywhere.
Go and tell your boss we said that.
- Hello, brother.
- Betty, what...?
You think you're the only one
who can scare people by being crazy?
You may have fooled my mother, but not me.
I'm gonna bring you down.
Because I catch bad men.
I caught Clifford Blossom.
I caught the Sugarman.
I caught the Black Hood.
And you know what they all have in common?
They're dead.
Consider yourself warned.
God, why didn't you call me last night?
I would have brought you blankets.
And you would've tried to stay.
Are you sure you're not gonna get arrested
for trespassing
or protesting without a permit?
No.
That's the beauty of all this, Betty.
If Sheriff Keller or his goons try
and manhandle teens
peacefully trying to save their school,
it'll look ugly.
Not to mention probably go viral, which...
[sighs]
At this point,
is publicity I would welcome.
Also, no one's gonna mess
with those guys there.
Good point. I have some student council
obligations with Veronica.
But I'll be back later tonight, okay?
Go get them, Tracy Flick.
[Josie] We live in uncertain times.
But here's one thing I'm very certain of:
My girl Ronnie here,
along with her running mate, Betty Cooper,
has my vote to be Riverdale High's
next president and vice president.
And, of course, we remind everyone,
especially the women,
to vote and be heard this election.
[crowd cheering]
♪ Now, you have heard
Of women's rights ♪
♪ And how we tried to reach new heights ♪
♪ If we're all created equal ♪
♪ That's us, too ♪
[crowd cheering]
Yeah
♪ Well, sure, some men bowed down
And called us Missus ♪
♪ Let us hang the wash out
And wash the dishes ♪
♪ But when the time rolled around
To elect a president ♪
♪ What did they say, sister? ♪
♪ Oh, we were suffering until suffrage ♪
♪ Not a woman here could vote
No matter what her age ♪
♪ Then the 19th Amendment struck down
That restrictive rule, yeah ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
Okay, what's going on?
[music stops]
- Where did you get this information?
- Doesn't matter.
It's the truth, isn't it?
I don't understand.
I told you
that your dad would get a job offer.
You mean your half-hearted bribe?
Yeah, too little, too late.
B, wait.
This is insane.
Thanks for the intel, Josie.
No problem.
The Lodges hurt a lot of people this year.
Your family, my family.
We girls gotta stick together.
That day when Weatherbee announced
that Southside High was closing,
you acted like you didn't know.
When my parents asked me to help them,
- I didn't feel like I could say no.
- Of course you could've.
You could've told your parents that you
didn't wanna be their accomplice,
or you could've told us the truth.
Instead, you played us like fools.
No, I was trying to keep them honest.
That's why I started working with them.
- You have to believe me.
- Even if I did...
I can't be your running mate anymore.
You know that.
I can't trust you, V.
Veronica?
Rough day on the campaign trail?
- How did you find out?
- Weatherbee called.
He read me the flyer
that's going around school.
See why we asked you
to keep a low profile?
And instead, you're running
for student council president? Why?
Because, Mom...
I'm out there, every day,
facing what you and Daddy have done,
what we've done.
And maybe if I'm their president,
people at school,
like Ethel Muggs or Jughead or...
Or even Betty... will stop looking at me
like I'm just the daughter of criminals.
Like I'm a criminal, too.
We're out there fighting a holy war, Mom.
I need something I can use as a shield.
Against everything that's coming our way.
Protection from everybody out there
who hates us.
Who's out for our blood.
[Alice] Stop right there, young lady.
Come in here now.
Is it true that you snuck
into your brother's room
to torment him with a Zippo lighter?
And what exactly is this for?
Oh, my God. You creep. What did you do,
go through my dresser drawers?
I was looking for the lighter
- and found all your secret toys.
- Why do you have this Cabaret wig?
She wears it
when she has sex with Jughead.
Is that true, Elizabeth?
I...
How would you even know that?
I was guessing.
Guessing?
Betty. What...?
Is it...? Is it true?
Are you-?
Are you and Jughead...?
Yeah, Mom, we are.
Last man standing.
What happened to no Serpent left behind?
They were claiming frostbite. They'll be
back after some coffee and they warm up.
Too bad. I got a dozen burgers.
Guess they're all yours now.
Come on, it's just you and me. I won't
tell anyone you broke your hunger strike.
So, uh...
just like clockwork,
I got a call from Hiram.
- What's he offering?
- You know how they're saying SoDale
will mostly be low-income housing?
Well, apparently, there'll be
a few penthouses at the top.
It would be more than enough space
for all of us. Your mom, Jellybean.
Just like you always wanted.
Just imagine me...
standing on that balcony
and looking over a prison.
In the same spot that my friends
and I used to go to school.
And Jellybean, growing up in a town...
where her best hope, her only hope,
aside from getting the hell out,
is to work at the prison?
[grunts]
It's not right.
- What'd you say to him?
- Nothing. I hung up
and went to Pop's and got some burgers.
I was hoping to see Jughead.
He's still at Southside High, Mom,
chained up.
You may not believe
in what he's fighting for...
I'm not sure he's fighting
for anything, Dad.
I think he's fighting against Mr. Lodge,
like people in this town who are afraid.
- Archie.
- Afraid? Afraid of what?
Afraid of having a vision, of seeing
what has to be done and doing it.
I hope you're not referring
to your father.
This man who broke rocks
when he was in school
to support his family
when his dad was sick.
A man who saw what had
to be done and did it,
and built a business out of nothing.
One that pays for this house
and the food you eat.
For your information, your father
had and has a vision for Riverdale,
one that doesn't end up
with everyone working in a penal colony.
You don't have to side with your dad.
You can side with Hiram,
even though he's a crook
and has no intention
of letting your father out.
You can do that. That is your right.
But I'll be damned if I'm gonna sit here
and listen to you disrespect him.
Betty, I have to ask.
- Are you being safe with Jughead?
- Yes, Mom.
- Of course.
- Well, that's something.
Because, look,
when I was your age, I wasn't always.
But you need to be.
And I am very well acquainted
with how alluring the Jones men are.
Whoa. Wait. Mom, did you and FP...?
I mean, is it possible
that FP is Chic's dad?
Absolutely not.
But Chic is a part of our family.
He's your brother.
I know that he's odd and damaged.
I see that. I'm not blind.
But for the past 25 years,
he hasn't had anyone to love him.
He's dangerous.
Mom, don't forget what he did.
I will never forget, Betty.
But Chic needs us.
[Cheryl] Dr. Masters?
- Any updates on my nana?
- Yes, we just got her panel back.
There was a paralytic toxin
in her bloodstream.
Tannis root. Which is strange,
because it's so rare.
Your mom and uncle have caught your nana
on more than one occasion
chewing Tannis root
she grows in your greenhouse.
So, it's more of her sundowner syndrome.
We'll keep her another day,
then she'll return home.
To my mother and uncle?
You don't understand...
Cheryl. There you are.
Looking a little worse for wear.
Poor dear hasn't slept in days.
Why don't we stop bothering Dr. Masters
and I'll take you home?
Come on.
Sorry.
Mom says we should bury the hatchet.
So, for her sake, how about a truce?
[scoffs]
Why should I believe you when all
you've done is try to get rid of me?
If I really wanted
to get rid of you, Chic...
I would go to the sheriff's office
and explain to him
how you brained a man in our kitchen.
You're not gonna do that.
You see, I never touched that body, Betty.
Or the car. Or went
through his phone, or called his contacts.
I didn't go to the sewer pipe.
It's not my fingerprints or hair
they're gonna find.
Maybe I should call the police, tell them
what my sister is capable of doing.
You wouldn't dare.
I'm not comfortable
being in a room with someone
who's done those things.
It scares me, Betty.
You scare me. Can't you see that?
You're scaring me, Betty.
You're scaring me.
I think I figured it out.
You paralyzed Nana Rose
with the Tannis root
and pushed her down the stairs.
You've gone mad.
That's all there is to it.
You have lost your mind and...
And you leave us no choice.
What do you mean, no choice?
But it's all right.
We're gonna make you all better.
All better.
Every hour that passes that Jughead
is out there is bad for business.
Time to remove Jughead
and his fellow Serpents by force.
Grown-ups after teenagers?
Wouldn't that be bad?
If Sheriff Keller and his men do it, yes.
But boys, led bravely by you?
The wrestling team.
No one would be too upset by that.
I can't.
I'm sorry, I won't.
Archie, you made a promise to me.
An oath to this family in this very room.
- You break it, there will be consequences.
- I understand.
So... you'll help me?
Yes, sir.
But I hope you can prove
your loyalty to me in return.
And how would I do that?
By releasing my dad
from all commitments to Lodge Industries.
[chanting] Save our school.
Save our school. Save our school.
Send a car by the station.
Cops may let you by, but you come in here,
and I'll knock you down.
Dad, don't. They'll throw you in jail.
Don't give them an excuse.
I'm sorry, Jughead.
Me, too.
I'm not gonna fight you, Archie.
Look around.
Now people know what Hiram's doing.
What's happening here.
This fight is not gonna go away.
We're not going to go away.
So, go on. Cut us down.
I want them to see you do it.
Do you think it made any difference?
Us freezing our asses off?
Definitely.
Every revolution starts somewhere.
Good.
'Cause I've been thinking.
We lost Southside High.
I don't want to lose Riverdale High, too.
And you've not heard more unlikely words
come from my mouth, but...
[sighs]
I wanna run for student body president.
And I want you to be my co-president.
- I know that you and Veronica...
- Okay.
- Really? Just like that?
- Just like that.
I'm in, Jug.
There is no me and Veronica.
You have to do me a favor, though.
You have to let me stay here.
I can't stay in the same house
as Chic anymore.
Okay.
[Mary laughing]
- What's going on?
- Your pal Hiram Lodge called.
He's letting your dad out of his contract.
Well, I never doubted your mom
for a second. Knew she'd do it.
Wow, that's...
- That's great.
- Yeah, and another thing.
- We've been talking...
- I'll stick around for a while.
Help your dad
with some more unfinished business.
That contract was the last thing
holding him back.
From what?
I'm gonna run for mayor.
Against the Lodges. Come what may.
[doorbell rings]
Mrs. Blossom, hi.
I'm looking for Cheryl. She wasn't
at the hospital with her nana.
No, she's gone.
Boarding school in Switzerland.
All girls. She left just last night.
[chuckles] Mrs. Blossom,
that doesn't make any sense.
Don't come here again.
[shivering]
Oh, you poor child.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
- Sister Woodhouse is going to help you.
- Thank you, Sister Woodhouse.
Yes, she's going to rid you
of all those naughty demons.
The ones making you think
such awful, unnatural thoughts.
Today, you must rest.
Tomorrow, the real work...
the conversion begins.