- Previously on Riverdale:
- The Conway Murders?
- They were a family of five.
- I found justice.
What if Mr. Svenson wasn't the Black Hood?
The Black Hood could be alive.
My dad, he might be the Black Hood.
Don't know. I've seen your father
sneak around Thistlehouse.
Lodge is a problem.
Did you have anything to do
with Poppa Poutine's death?
Small Fry is looking for payback.
Penny, you wanna deal drugs?
It's not gonna be with the Serpents.
- That used to be my Serpent tattoo.
- You nuts? She will be back.
Our adversaries, the Ghoulies, have
been released. They want Serpent blood.
Midge?
- You're dead!
- Mr. Fogarty. Come with us.
- I didn't kill her.
- Didn't you?
His release is going
to make a lot of people very unhappy.
- The Circle is disbanded.
- You're not paying us. Hiram is.
- Fangs Fogarty is being released.
- What?
They wanna rip Fangs apart.
We need help, Archie.
Okay, Dad. Let's talk.
I swear, Mother.
If this is one of your callers...
I suggest you run whilst you still can.
I only miss when I mean to.
Help us! We need a doctor!
- Ma'am.
- Wait your turn.
- He was shot.
- Step back...
- He's dying!
- Hey! What's going on here?
- My friend was shot.
- Hey, get me a gurney.
Be careful.
Let's go.
Hang in there. Hang in there.
- Where are you going?
- To find the guy who shot Fangs.
You're not going. Not with people rioting.
You're angry, you want justice? So do I.
You've got a fallen soldier,
and we need to talk to his family.
That's part of being a leader.
- Some leader I am.
- Don't go down that road.
All right. Come on. Come on.
Cheryl?
The Black Hood just attacked me.
Oh, my God.
Was it my dad?
Based on waistline,
it could've been him, yes.
Luckily, I was able to get
to my archery set and hunting cape.
- You didn't kill him, did you?
- No. I shot to wound.
Hit him in the right shoulder. He's fled
into the woods where I plan to track him.
Just in case he escapes my clutches,
be forewarned:
Now that he's a maimed animal,
he's operating on instinct,
ready to lash out
and kill anyone in his path.
Even his loved ones.
Here, include that.
- Elizabeth, thank goodness.
- Mom.
- Are you okay? Have you seen Dad?
- He's out covering the riots.
Where are you? The streets aren't safe.
You need to get here.
- I'm on my way, but stay put, okay?
- I'm not going anywhere.
It's a big night for The Register.
If it bleeds, it leads.
Get over here now.
- Hey, Arch...
- It's just me, Mr. Andrews.
I was about to slip out.
Is something wrong?
On the news, it said a riot broke out
down at the sheriff's station.
Where is Archie?
- Where's Reggie?
- I thought he was with you.
We got separated. Reggie had a gun.
He didn't shoot Fangs. I tackled him.
- Why have a gun?
- I can guess who put the idea in his head.
But we gotta find him.
Some Serpents saw Reggie with the gun.
They're gonna go after him.
Kev, Moose. We'll head to Reggie's house.
Everyone else, fan out.
Call if you find him.
Archie was there
when that Serpent got shot.
- I don't know what he's caught up in.
- I'm coming with you.
Good evening, Mr. Andrews.
I'm here to pick up Miss Lodge.
Thank you, Andre.
Yes. Bring her directly home.
Okay. Now that we know Veronica's safe,
one of Minetta's deputies
will take you over to The Register.
Alice is waiting.
There's no way of controlling
what could happen.
Hiram, it's a huge gamble.
No, the fire's started, mi amor.
Chaos is good for us.
We have the pieces in place
to restore order. Fred doesn't.
Andre will keep watch on Veronica.
- Where will you be?
- Out with another deputy.
Hiram.
You're not keeping anything from me,
right?
Don't start doubting me now.
- Excuse me. How's Fangs?
- He's still in surgery.
I wanna talk to him
as soon as he wakes up.
Sheriff Minetta.
- Shouldn't you looking for who shot Fangs?
- There's a manhunt underway.
Your Serpent pals
aren't making things easy.
Rioting, carousing, terrorizing.
Already arrested a few.
Fangs wouldn't have a slug in his gut
if you had done your job.
I don't know the details of your parole,
but I'm certain harassing an officer
would violate them.
Jug?
Mr. Lodge. It's me, Reggie.
I need your help. Someone shot Fangs.
It wasn't me.
But I was there
and the Southsiders think I did it.
That's unfortunate, Reggie.
But I'm afraid I can't help you.
Oh, my God... Is that Mrs. Klump?
Andre, stop the car.
That's Midge's mom.
- Miss Veronica, wait.
- Mrs. Klump?
- Are you okay?
- I may have killed that boy.
Archie, what is going on?
- The Serpents are going nuts.
- Yeah. Reggie shot Fangs.
No, I was with Reggie. It wasn't him.
You need to call off your crew.
We're leaving Reggie's house.
- They find him?
- No. We're headed to the school.
- That's where Mrs. Mantle said they were.
- Okay. I'm on my way.
- Whenever you're ready.
- As a mayoral candidate,
it's important to take charge
in times of crisis.
Like this riot,
which I believe was brought about
by the actions of the Black Hood.
Which is why I would like to offer
a bounty.
One million dollars to whomever
can deliver the Black Hood.
Alive or preferably dead.
Synced & corrected by MaxPayne
== https://subscene.com ==
A bounty? What are you talking about?
Is that even legal?
The Black Hood is a shooter
on the streets of Riverdale.
- He tried to kill one of your classmates...
- No. The Black Hood did not shoot Fangs.
Excuse me, how would you know that?
Did anyone see the Black Hood
at the sheriff's station?
Why are you being protective
of a murderer?
Cheryl. Any new leads?
- Where are you?
- At The Register. Why?
He's exited the forest and headed
for the houses beyond the pines.
Maybe even yours.
- I have to go.
- Wait, cousin.
Do not go into that house alone.
I have to find my dad
before anyone else does.
Otherwise, he's a dead man walking.
That's gotta be Southsiders.
- Serpent scum.
- Settle down. We're outmanned and unarmed.
- I'm not gonna hide.
- I'm with Moose.
All right, but it's us
against who knows how many.
So, if we're gonna do this,
we gotta gear up.
Ronnie, can I call you back?
A riot broke out.
Yes, Archie, I know.
I was out in the middle of it.
I thought you were at my house.
Not only did I brave the streets,
I delivered Fangs' shooter, Mrs. Klump,
- to the authorities.
- Mrs. Klump shot Fangs?
- Can you blame her?
- I gotta tell the Serpents.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
Mom? Sheriff Minetta.
Veronica. What are you doing?
You're supposed to be at home.
Andre's in the car.
We had to make a detour.
Good Lord, Mom.
Are you and Daddy trying to turn Riverdale
into Gotham City?
Serpents! Stop!
Well, fellas. Looks like we found
some bulldogs to put down.
Sweet Pea. I swear,
Reggie didn't shoot Fangs.
- It was Mrs. Klump.
- I saw Mantle with a gun.
Then you saw me tackle him
before he got a shot off.
It was Midge's mom.
She's down at the station.
And Fangs is clinging to life.
Whether it was Reggie or Mrs. Klump
who pulled the trigger,
a Northsider put him there!
You took our friend.
Our land.
You'll take everything
if we give you the chance.
So, now you get to watch
as we burn your school to the ground.
What do you boys think
you're doing to my school?
Hello? Dad?
Dad.
- You're too late, Jughead.
- Try Mad Max-ing your way through a riot.
- What happened?
- Weatherbee shut us down.
- Kicked our asses out.
- The Serpents took off again.
- Where?
- They went down Fernleaf.
- Midge Klump's house.
- Why there?
To trash it. I told them Mrs. Klump
shot Fangs, not Reggie.
Jughead, you have to coax them
off the ledge.
- I'm on it.
- Wait.
- Have you spoken to Betty?
- She's with her mom. Keep in touch.
You, too.
- Hello?
- Archie, it's Pop.
I've got a friend of yours here.
I think he needs help.
Hello?
Betty, it's FP. I'm at Riverdale General.
Is Jug with you?
Mr. Jones. No, I don't know where he is.
If you see him,
tell him I'm looking for him.
Of course I will.
Also, uh, Betty, they just brought
your old man into to ER.
My dad?
Is he hurt badly?
He's bleeding quite a bit.
You want me to check on him?
No. That's okay, Mr. Jones. I'm on my way.
Where do you plan on getting the million
dollars to pay for this lunatic bounty?
- Your father has secret funds.
- My ass he does.
If Daddy thinks he can use my money
for one of his Machiavellian ploys,
he better think again, because I'm taking
back what I got from the St. Claire.
Your father already told you.
He put that money in a trust for you.
He stole it, you mean.
Veronica! Veronica!
You're wasting your time.
Your money is not in there.
Veronica, just open the door
and we can talk about this.
I didn't know where else to go.
- Mr. Lodge left me hanging.
- Wait, Reggie.
I know he paid you
to trash the Whyte Wyrm.
- But did he put you up to this?
- Guys. Outside.
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Serpents. They're coming for me.
- What's up?
- Jughead, where are you guys?
Just got the Serpents back to the Wyrm.
Mrs. Klump's house is secure.
What's wrong?
If the Serpents are with you,
then who is out here at Pop's?
Oh, crap.
Jug, looks like the Ghoulies
are back in town.
Damn it. Nobody's answering
at the sheriff's station.
Looks like we're on our own.
We should be fine, as long as everybody...
Everybody get away from the windows!
Stay down!
- Do you have a gun in here, Pop?
- No.
I had my fill of gunfire back in the war.
But I learned a trick in the riots of '79.
I have Mr. Lodge's leftover liquor
from poker night.
If you can get to the roof
through the crawlspace...
I like how you're thinking, Pop.
Anyone, come out and play!
We got some new toys to show you.
Hey!
Come on.
Hit me!
All right, now it's a party.
Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
Get out of here.
- Mr. Keller, I thought you resigned.
- I turned in my badge,
- but not the cruiser yet.
- How did you know we're here?
Jug called, said you were in trouble.
I called your dad.
Right when Kevin called.
We're not letting this town
go down without a fight.
Hot Riverdale Dads to the rescue.
- I can't just sit here.
- Sweet Pea. You're staying put!
You said it yourself.
The Ghoulies are back.
We will deal with them.
As soon as my dad gets back...
You're not our leader all of a sudden?
That's right.
- You're just the guy that got Fangs shot.
- Watch it.
Fangs might die.
The Ghoulies are out for our blood,
because of a drag race you started.
An hour.
That's all I'm asking for, Sweet Pea.
This is utterly vile.
Daddy has written the story
about the affair you and Fred had.
What was he planning to do,
publish that in The Register,
and drag you both through the mud?
Fred's running on family values.
I'm the law and order candidate.
Your father believes an October Surprise
would hurt me,
but I'd survive, and it would utterly
destroy Fred's campaign.
- You were in on this?
- There's a game plan.
What kind of man would do this
to his own wife?
I'll tell you. The kind of man who always
has someone else to take the risk,
to stand in the line of fire,
to run for mayor.
That's what you are to him.
A means to an end. Kindling for the fire.
Oh, no, Veronica.
Your father would never put us
in harm's way.
The fact that you still believe that,
after everything he's done,
chills me, Mom.
Pop Tate. I heard there was an incident
at the diner.
Rioters were here.
But Fred Andrews showed up with Tom Keller
and FP Jones. They saved us.
Helped defend the Chock'lit Shoppe
from the Ghoulies.
- Everyone's calling them heroes.
- I see.
Thank you, Pop. And, uh...
- I'm glad you're okay.
- All right.
Sorry. We're not serving right now.
That wasn't Hiram Lodge
you were speaking with, was it?
It was.
He's an old friend of my father's.
Wouldn't happen to know
where he lives, would you?
Excuse me.
Um, my dad is here. Hal Cooper.
What room is he in?
Uh...
- Two-twenty one, just down the hall.
- Thank you.
Dad.
Oh.
We keep missing each other.
- You murdered Dr. Masters.
- He asked too many questions.
There's no method to the killing now?
No grand design?
- You're just a run-of-the-mill psychopath?
- You need to come home,
so we can talk and finish this.
Fine.
You don't scare me.
Your mother's here.
What?
- Mom's there?
- If you're not home in ten minutes,
or if you call the police,
I will slit your mother's throat.
No.
- Hello?
- Hello, lover boy. It's your old gal pal.
Penny.
You picked a bad time.
Oh, I heard. Riverdale,
burning to the ground. It's tragic.
How about we meet up and talk about it?
Hmm? Your old hangout, by the docks?
- Why would I do that?
- If you don't,
I'll start carving up
your girlfriend's face.
- Betty?
- Oh, please! Ponytail's a snooze.
No, I mean, your Southside Smurfette.
- What do you think I should start with?
- Tell her to go to hell.
Maybe her tongue? Hmm? Come now.
And alone.
It'll just be me and Pinkie here.
Mom? Mom, where are you?
Betty. Thank God. I've been calling you.
Where have you been?
Mom, is Dad here? Is he...?
- Yeah, honey. Why?
- Where is he?
- What's going on? What?
- We have to leave. Let's go.
Betty! You made it home.
Your dad has some crazy idea
to show us old home movies.
I figured we indulge him, since we're
practically on lockdown anyway.
What's wrong?
Well, I'm just happy we're all here.
As a family.
Sit down, Betty.
I think you're really going to enjoy this.
I'm making this movie so we never
forget what your daddy sacrificed for us.
You do love your daddy, don't you, Harold?
Yes, Mom.
And you want your daddy
to keep living with us?
- Yes, Mom.
- I don't understand. What are we watching?
- Is that you, Hal?
- It is.
Your daddy did something
very noble, Harold.
He took care of that Conway family.
They were sinners.
- And what happens to sinners?
- Sinners have to die.
- Oh, my God.
- What is this, a snuff film?
Shut the hell up, Alice,
for once in your life.
That's right.
Now, that little Conway boy who survived,
they're gonna ask him
who killed his family.
He needs to point out somebody.
Anybody. But not Daddy.
Because we don't want Daddy
to be taken away from us, do we?
No, I love my daddy.
So, you have to help him.
Make sure that when they ask
the Conway boy who he saw kill his family,
make sure he doesn't say Daddy.
Can you do that, Harold? Convince him?
I think so.
You're a good boy, Hal.
Your father let him escape, but you?
You will do better. You must do better.
Take out your tape recorder, Alice.
I need you to record this.
The Conways. The family that was
murdered 40 years ago?
Yes. Oh, my God.
Take it out!
Now I wanna tell my story.
No, our story, really.
First, to clear something up:
Your Great-Grandpappy Cooper wasn't
murdered by his brother like some dog.
He was the killer.
He killed Great-Grandpappy Blossom
and then took on the Cooper name
to create a new identity for himself.
For us.
What does that have to do
with the Conways?
The Conways knew our secret.
Mr. Conway blackmailed my father,
your grandpappy.
So, Grandpa killed them.
They were sinners, Betty.
Even the children?
Well, there was one survivor.
The Conways' boy Joseph.
Mr. Svenson.
Who you convinced to accuse
an innocent man.
Joseph was easy to manipulate.
- As a boy and as a man.
- What are you telling us? Hal? That...?
That I have a darkness, Alice.
The same darkness my father had,
the same darkness his father had.
And now, it lives in Betty.
No.
Our daughter.
Who am I, Betty?
Say it.
Say who I am!
You're the Black Hood.
That's right.
Now say what I did.
You... shot Mr. Andrews.
You... killed Ms. Grundy...
the Sugarman, Midge, Dr. Masters.
- But, the debate...
- Was not me.
I can't take credit for that.
- How's Veronica doing with all this?
- She's in lockdown at The Pembrooke.
For all of Mr. Lodge's talk
about law and order,
he was nowhere to be seen tonight.
I just went out to try to find you.
I'm gonna take a shower.
I'm gonna lock up.
Are you okay?
Thought about going pro after high school.
- Dad!
- What?
No!
Dad. Dad.
I'm good. Tom Keller made us put these on
before we went to the diner.
I'm good.
No. Archie, no!
Dad, why did you become the Black Hood?
Because this is a town of sinners, Betty.
And...
Sinners have to die.
Your speech at the Jubilee...
Riverdale must do better.
We must do better.
You will do better. You must do better.
Reminded me of a promise
that I made my mother.
That this town will do better.
We must do better.
So, I picked up my father's sword
and I continued the work
that he and my grandfather started.
The purging of sin.
No. None of this makes any sense.
Dad, why did you want this recorded?
I want everyone to understand
when they find us.
Hiya, Jones.
Toni. Are you okay?
Jughead, she's not alone.
Surprise!
You said it was gonna be
the two of us.
I never go without backup anymore.
Not after what you did to me.
Besides, we need to talk.
All of us.
There's nothing to talk about.
- I'm taking Toni and we're leaving.
- Not so fast.
I've been waiting to see you again
for a long time.
Get back, you hobgoblin.
I brought backup, too. Like I said,
I'm taking Toni and we're leaving.
Untie her, you Serpent hag.
Take her then.
But remember, when all your friends
are dead, I tried giving you a chance.
Why do you keep coming back?
What do you want?
The Southside. There's money
to be made here in The Town With Pep.
If you're not afraid of
getting your hands dirty.
You partnered with the Ghoulies
to sell drugs on the Southside.
Bingo. So, here's the offer I want you
to take back to your dad and your tribe.
The Serpents ship out tonight,
or it's a showdown
with the Ghoulies at Pickens Park.
I'm fine either way.
Hello. I'm here to see Mr. Lodge.
I'm sorry, he's not available.
Are his lovely wife and beautiful daughter
at home?
This is a game of nerves,
and clearly you've lost yours.
I would rather have lost my nerve than my
mind, which clearly you and Daddy have.
That October Surprise wouldn't destroy
Fred's campaign, it would ruin his life.
Oh, God. Who is it?
You may know my father.
Goes by the name Poppa Poutine.
He told me if he was ever to be murdered,
not to take the life of the man
who killed him,
but to take the lives of those
that man loved the most.
- Mom.
- Mija, run! Run!
Stay behind me.
It's time we end the Ghoulie scourge,
and that traitor Penny Peabody.
- Permanently.
- Sweet Pea, two hours ago,
your fight was with Reggie Mantle.
Now you want us to go to war over
territory we don't even control anymore?
This is Hiram Lodge's problem, not ours.
You're gonna hand over
Sunnyside Trailer Park
- to Penny and the Ghoulies?
- Toni, I don't want us to die.
A rumble with the Ghoulies?
It's a suicide-run.
- Better than a coward's death.
- Don't call me a coward!
That's enough!
I just got a call
from the sheriff's office.
Fangs, uh...
He didn't make it. He's gone.
Fangs is dead?
And we will mourn him. We will.
But first, we will honor him.
From what I just heard,
we need to put it to a vote.
All those against going to war
with the Ghoulies?
And all those for giving them hell
on the battlefield tomorrow?
Well, Hal, I can't say I'm surprised.
Mom.
I always knew you were a mama's boy.
- What did you say?
- You heard me.
I knew it. I knew you couldn't do anything
for yourself.
- Mom, whatever you're doing, I wouldn't.
- I'm pointing out
that your father can't do anything right.
Not even be a serial killer.
Cleansing the town of sin? Really, Hal?
- You're the damn sinner.
- Mom.
What are you gonna do?
Kill the entire town? Whoever's jaywalked?
What did Fred Andrews do
to deserve to get shot?
- He was an adulterer.
- Then why don't you kill yourself?
You had a fling with Penelope Blossom.
Or me, for that matter.
I stepped out on you with FP,
who, in every way that you are not,
is a real man.
This is a mistake.
You can see that, right?
We'd be going in blind, Dad.
Will you listen to me for two seconds?
For all we know,
- the Ghoulies outnumber us 100-to-1.
- Don't you think I know that?
Boy, I've been doing this a lot longer
than you have. And we voted.
If we're going down,
we're going down fighting.
As far as being outnumbered,
I'll rally the reserves. They'll fight.
- This is Hiram.
- Fangs getting arrested,
the riots...
the Ghoulies showing up the night
of the riots, Penny in tow.
None of this is happenstance.
Jughead, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
You've been buying up everything
you could, but you couldn't buy us.
So, you paid the Ghoulies and Penny...
to go to war with the Serpents,
to finally get rid of us once and for all.
How much is this costing you?
- I'm hanging up now.
- Because I have a counter-offer.
Mr. Lodge?
I'm listening.
Andre?
Veronica? Hermione?
There's another dead body in the study.
It's your mess, Daddy. You clean it up.
It was him, Arch.
My dad was the Black Hood.
How did you...?
Did you see him leave my house?
- He tried to shoot my dad again.
- When?
An hour ago.
No, no, no. That's impossible.
He was... He was here with us.
- Jug.
- Betty.
I'm happy to hear your voice.
Me, too, Jug. You have no idea.
I just wanna let you know I love you.
I'll never stop loving you.
- What are you saying? Where are you?
- Where is he?
I'll see you soon.
The sacrificial lamb arrives.
I'll remind you of the deal that I made
with your boss, Hiram Lodge.
I hand myself over to you
and there's no bloodshed tomorrow.
Getting you out of the picture
is more important to him
than all-out Serpent annihilation.
Thirty-to-1. Are you that afraid of me?
The scary thing is what we're gonna do
to your girlfriend when we find her.
You're a true hero, Jughead.
Let your dying thought be
that your sacrifice was for nothing.
And that come morning, Riverdale
as you know it will cease to exist.
Don't finish him off yet, guys.
I want my pound of flesh first.
- Betty, are you and your mom okay?
- Is Jughead with you?
- He's at the trailer. Why?
- I'm worried about him.
He called to say how much he loves me,
and it sounded like he was saying goodbye
for good.
Toni. Where was Penny hiding out?
Jug?
Minetta delivered the bodies to the
coroner's office, tagged as riot victims.
No one's gonna be asking us questions.
I am so sorry.
I just thank God that neither of you
were hurt.
I found your October Surprise file.
Well, your mother understands
the costs of winning...
better than almost anyone.
Isn't that right, mi amor?
I realized something.
There will always be an October Surprise
with you.
And another. And another.
But while Mom may volunteer
to be your collateral damage...
- I won't.
- What did I always teach you?
Never lose sight of the bigger picture.
I'm not the one who's lost sight, Daddy.
Where is he? Where's Jug?
Guys...