Previously on Riverdale...
This is the Black Hood.
I want to cleanse Riverdale of sinners.
I can't keep doing this.
I need you to cut your
friends out of your life,
or I will, my way.
They'll consider re-opening
The Red and the Black
on two conditions.
One, no gangs. Two, no Jingle Jangle.
You can write about them,
but if I see trafficking
in either, we're done.
You should hang with the Serpents.
The Ghoulies get whiff that
you're alone and vulnerable...
Tall Boy was the one
who gave me this jacket.
It's finally time I start wearing it.
- Is that...
- Jingle Jangle.
Nick, I mean it, stop!
We didn't get much of
chance to talk last night.
I want Nick to pay... to
suffer, to burn in hell.
Give me another name.
Nick St. Clair.
In Riverdale, everyone wears a mask,
not just the Black Hood.
But every so often, the mask slips
and our true selves are laid
bare, for all the world to see.
Morning. You... you hungry?
You never have to ask me that.
Cool.
So we scramble to put it back on,
like a kid in a cheap Halloween costume,
but it's too late.
People have already
seen what's underneath...
And it's terrifying.
Oh, my God.
What? Here to finish what
your little friends started?
You're alive.
Yeah, and you tell that bitch Veronica
she's lucky I'm not pressing charges.
Nicholas, why aren't you dressed yet?
And who's this?
You're not safe here, okay? Any of you.
You need to go...
Nicholas St. Clair?
He is and I'm his father
is there a problem?
Well, there's been a
complaint made against him.
He's gonna have to come
down to the station.
You and your wife, as well.
You might wanna get dressed, son.
Should I ask what you're doing here?
I'm
making sure Nick got
what was coming to him.
Go home, Betty.
You didn't kill him.
Nick isn't one of Riverdale's sons.
And you'd already given
me the most wonderful gift.
When you said Nick's name,
in that moment of nakedness,
you let me see the real Betty.
And she was beautiful, and righteous.
Judge, jury, executioner...
No, no, that's not. I'm...
Now that I've seen your true self,
Betty, the real work can begin.
What do you mean?
_
Penelope, thank you for coming.
We called as soon as Cheryl told us.
And I appreciate that,
I just wish you'd
stopped her from talking
to Sheriff Keller.
Lord knows what Cheryl did or said
to the St. Clair boy to provoke him.
According to Veronica, nothing.
Hermione. Hiram.
I want this handled discreetly.
Well, I'm confident that the
St. Clairs feel the same way.
Then it's settled.
I'll talk to that idiot Keller
and tell him we won't
be pressing charges.
After all,
nothing really happened to Cheryl.
Cheryl, I'm... so sorry.
Don't be silly. I'm used to it.
And besides, you heard what Mommy said.
Nothing really happened to me.
- Nick roofied you, he tried...
- I'm fine,
Veronica. Everything's fine.
If everything's fine,
why did we call Sheriff
Keller and make a statement?
A momentary lapse in sanity.
I mean, can you even imagine?
Me, facing off against Nick St.
Clair in a courtroom battle royale?
- I'd be a laughing stock.
- Cheryl, wait.
It's not just you.
He's done it to other girls,
I mean, hell, he even
tried to do it to me.
The night before the open house.
Did you tell your parents?
And yet you were happy to fill them in
on my after-dark-drama, weren't you?
Well, I won't be a puppet
for your thirst for vengeance.
You want justice?
You go after Nick in court, Veronica.
Thanks for letting me sleep over.
Now on to the next crashpad
until my uncle stops locking me out.
My trailer is your trailer.
- Last night was...
- A PG-13 grope-session?
Ooh. Way to knock a guy down a peg.
Look, cards on the table.
You're not over Betty,
and I'm not interested in
being anybody's rebound.
Besides,
I'm more into girls anyways.
Roger that.
I needed to clear my head and I did.
And I realized that this
is just a sick game to him.
Psychological torture.
So,
I'm done. With the Black Hood.
With his letters, with his Simon Says.
So, what happens when he calls again?
I won't answer.
I can't... keep playing. I can't.
- Didn't he threaten Polly?
- He did and I talked to her.
The people at the Farm are gonna
help her disappear for a while.
- Just until it's safe again.
- Yeah, whenever that is.
And what about Jughead and Veronica?
We have to tell them the truth.
And we will. I'll tell them. Let's just,
you know, let things settle first.
Make sure it's all over.
- Mom.
- Dad.
Riverdale's best and brightest, huh?
Alice, thank you for hosting.
Of course, Mayor McCoy.
When I heard what
happened at Nick's party,
I decided that we should come together
to deal with this motley crew of liars,
dope-fiends, and fornicators.
Except for my Betty, who was
smart enough to leave the party
before it descended into
a bacchanalian free for all
Oh, my God. Mom, please don't.
Oh great, here we go
Saint Betty and Succubus Veronica.
So, this is for clarity, Alice.
You're hosting this little
get-together to what?
You know, I may ave taken Jingle Jangle,
but she's the one who
had a psychotic break
Cut her some slack, Veronica.
She just broke up with Jughead
What? Hashtag Bughead is no more?
And Betty didn't tell me?
Careful throwing stones
there, acid-queen Alice.
I'm not the only one in this room
that knows the story behind that mugshot
that your daughter printed in her paper.
Well I, for one, would like to know
who brought the Jingle
Jangle to the party?
Reginald, not a single
word out of your mouth
until we get a lawyer.
No, all Reggie needs
to tell us, Melinda,
is how he acquired it.
Some gang member who
deals on the Southside...
Oh, my God, you have a dealer?
Once again, Mayor,
the Southside is the
source of all our problems.
Was he a Serpent? Does
he go to Southside High?
- I think so, yeah.
- What does it matter?
Not all Serpents are drug dealers.
- Archie, not helping.
- Look,
we shouldn't have taken the JJ,
but Nick's the one who
asked Reggie to get it
and then pushed it on us.
He's the one who should
be in the hot seat.
I mean, he's the one who roofied
Cheryl and tried to assault her.
Prosecuting Nick St.
Clair would be difficult
given that all witnesses were high.
Yeah, but Josie and
I saw Nick with Cheryl
the night after the party, and
neither of us were on Jingle Jangle.
The drug stays in your
system for three days.
So if I drug tested you right now,
you'd have a credibility problem.
Josie, you took that drug?
You put that poison in your system,
knowing the way your father's
struggled with addiction?
I see.
From this moment on, bringing
the Southside under control
is my number one priority as mayor.
If it means razing it to the ground
or arresting every
single Serpent in sight,
starting at that high school,
so be it.
Let's go, Josephine,
now!
"People have associated this school with
the plagues of the Southside.
Drugs, gangs, violence.
But, like the Southside,
there is a community here.
And while the decay is real,
it is not irreversible."
I'm impressed, Jughead.
Where'd you find the time
to put out an issue of
The Red and the Black
while pledging the Southside Serpents?
I'm not blind.
We had a deal.
The Serpents...
They truly are a
community, Mr. Phillips.
A community of drug-dealers.
That's not the Serpents.
That's the Ghoulies.
That's my next article.
Jughead, when you said...
_
Uh, will you excuse
me? Just two seconds.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Mr. Phillips.
Jug! Jug!
We gotta go, right now.
What the hell are you doing here?
Betty ask you to throw
some salt in the wound?
Mayor McCoy's about
to raid Southside High.
We gotta get you out of
here, right now, come on.
Toni!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Jug, you wanna help her?
You can't do that from
behind bars. Come on.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
What do you mean Nick did it to you?
He tried to.
After the penthouse party
that I nipped it in the bud.
Ugh, I hope Nick St. Clair
chokes on his silver spoon.
You need to tell someone.
My dad. Or your dad.
No, Kevin. My dad cannot know.
Have you ever seen The Godfather?
If my dad ever found
out what Nick did...
What? He'd put a horse's
head in Nick's bed?
Worse, he'd put Nick's head in
Mr. and Mrs. St. Clair's bed.
I don't want his blood on
my dad's hands or on mine.
Hey.
- Veronica, I...
- Don't even try,
Benedict Betty.
Chill, Kevin. She's not worth it.
I've done everything you've asked.
Why can't you leave me the hell alone?
Because we're not finished.
I spared Nick's life.
Because of me, you don't
have his blood on your hands.
If you don't help me,
you'll be responsible for far worse.
Riverdale's streets will run red.
Help you how?
While Keller and his men
hunt for low-level dealers,
we will go after the real sinner,
the drug maker,
someone who hides behind a name,
the Sugarman.
A corrupter of children who
deserves swift, brutal justice.
The fact that you're
asking me to find him
means that you can't.
I'm a school-newspaper reporter.
Who also happens to be
friends with the daughter
of the Sugarman's former
supplier, Clifford Blossom.
I'd start there.
And if I find him,
what will you do to him?
Don't ask questions you don't
want the answers to, Betty.
Bring me the identity of the
Sugarman, and I will put down my sword.
And if I don't? If I refuse?
Someone will be purified.
Don't test me on that.
- Jughead, calm down.
- Calm down?
Archie, Riverdale just
became a police state.
McCoy's convinced the Serpents
are dealing jingle-jangle.
Serpents don't deal that
stuff. The Ghoulies do.
- So, tell Mayor McCoy that.
- Oh, Mayor McCoy.
Do you mean the McCoy that just
arrested all my friends for no reason?
Why do you care anyway, man?
I thought you and Betty wanted
nothing to do with me, right?
I'm sorry about what
happened, and how it happened.
And as for Betty, you
should maybe talk to her.
I gotta go. Tall Boy wants to parley.
Sweet cousin, to what do I
owe this unannounced pleasure?
I just wanted to see how you were doing.
I'm... compartmentalizing.
But I also see right
through you, Invisible Woman.
I'm writing an article.
On Jingle Jangle inundating Riverdale.
- Have you ever heard of the Sugarman?
- Yeah, of course.
What?
As children, Mother told us tales
of how Daddy was friends
with the so-called Sugarman.
And if we were bad,
he'd sneak into our rooms at
night, steal us from our beds,
whisk us away, nevermore to be seen.
Cheryl, is it possible
that this man maybe worked
for your father's drug business?
Dear God, Betty, is there no memory,
however traumatic, you won't defile?
- I'm just trying to get to the truth.
- I've told you the truth..
The Sugarman was a poison confection
spun by my mother to scare children.
Like the sandman or Krampus.
Now, fly away, little bird.
Community service? Can't
you just ground me, Dad?
Community service was
Mayor McCoy's idea,
and it's a damn good one if you ask me.
You wanna put that trash in your body,
you can spend the day picking
up trash at Pickens Park.
I know Jug wasn't at your
Lollapalooza the other night,
but he does go to Southside High.
It's ground zero for that crap.
You talking to him,
checking in? How's he doing?
- Trying to.
- Yeah.
It was kind of like that
when I was trying to help FP.
I don't what it is. A
never-ending battle with those two.
I just hope with Jug
it's not a losing one.
Sit down, kid.
Business to discuss.
Tall Boy, what the hell
is this? Where are we?
You're in my house.
It's the House of the Dead.
Well, I'm sorry, who the hell are you?
Take it easy, Jughead.
Malachai speaks for the Ghoulies.
The heat on us and our ranks
depleted, our tribes need to unite,
and that's gonna be easier to do
if you endorse this partnership.
- Me?
- You're FP's son.
That carries weight, especially
with our younger members.
Tall Boy, they're the reason
Southside was even raided.
Them and their jingle-jangle.
- Chaos is how we thrive.
You'd better get used to it.
Are you seriously
gonna do this to my dad?
- You're supposed to be his right hand.
- The Northside declared war today.
Your old man ain't
here to call the shots.
And, yeah, I'm his right hand.
That makes me de facto
leader here and now. So...
things are changing, Jones.
Either you change with them...
or suffer the consequences.
Evolve or die, baby.
Evolve or die.
Sheriff Keller. The station
said you might be here.
I'm off the clock, Betty.
Just a few questions for a Blue
and Gold story on jingle-jangle.
All right.
One question, so, you'd
better make it good.
Have you ever heard of a
dealer called the Sugarman?
Have I heard of him? Well,
I know him. You know him.
The Sugarman, the Maple
Man, the Delivery Man,
he had about a million different
names, but it was always just one man.
Clifford Blossom.
But he's dead.
So, how is there still a
supply of jingle-jangle?
Jingle-jangle didn't hit the
streets until after Clifford died.
Truth is, anybody could
be the supplier now.
Good night, Betty.
Drafting your next savage takedown?
I don't expect you to believe
me, but I didn't mean what I said.
There's no sane excuse.
No, there isn't.
So, tell me, B...
what's the insane excuse?
So, to recap...
you're talking to a
serial killer on the reg...
and he's been puppet-mastering you?
I'll never forgive
myself for what I did, V.
To you, to Jug, to my mom.
Hell, even to Nick St. Clair.
Girl, I would've given Nick's name
and then happily treated
myself to a facial.
I still may. But, yes...
you're in a toxic relationship
with the Black Hood
- and you need to break up.
- Or I could turn the tables on him, V.
He says he'll go away
if I do one last thing...
find out who's behind the jingle-jangle.
Some creep called the Sugarman.
Okay. So, what's the problem?
If the Sugarman exists
and I find out who he is,
I can't just give up his name.
The Black Hood would kill him.
Drug dealer or not,
he's still a human being.
- Barely.
- I'm so close, V.
Will you help?
I'm in.
This isn't an alliance with the
Ghoulies. This is a hostile takeover.
God, who knows how long Tall Boy
has been planning on betraying us.
Maybe I stall, just until
Sweet Pea and Toni get out.
I just hope they'd rather go to
war with the Ghoulies than start...
- Jughead.
- Dealing jingle-jangle.
You joined the Serpents
to keep the peace.
My dad would never sit back and
let this happen, so, neither will I.
So, unless you have any better ideas...
Not me. But, dude, what you just said...
Start from the beginning, boys.
Hey, you can reprimand me for
joining the Serpents later,
but if we don't do something now...
there will be no more Serpents.
It'll just be the Ghoulies.
Ghoulies dress like fops,
but they're a nasty crew.
The Serpents have
survived worse, though.
Much worse. The only hitch is,
it sounds like you're outmanned,
which means you gotta avoid
bloodshed at all costs.
- I agree. A hundred percent.
- So, outthink them.
This is about territory.
If there's one thing Ghoulies love,
it's their crazy souped-up
retro cars and hearses.
You catch my Riverdale drift, boys?
Challenge them to a
street race, one-on-one.
But keep it on the DL. It's
illegal. It'll get you locked up.
- Go on.
- Set the terms of the race.
Their guy wins, the Serpents roll over.
But if we win, the Ghoulies back off.
And maybe you raise the stakes.
Whoever wins controls Southside High.
We get rid of the Ghoulies and
get rid of the jingle-jangle
and get McCoy off our back.
That's me, that's Jason,
and that's the Sugarman.
Remember? You'd tell us tales
of how he was friends with Daddy?
We were to stay up in our rooms
whenever he visited Thornhill?
Was he one of Daddy's
business associates?
Not maple syrup, but the
other kind of business?
After all you kept from me
about Daddy, about Jason's death,
is this another piece
of your cryptic puzzle?
As usual, Cheryl, I have no
idea what you're talking about.
I never told you any such stories.
As for your father's business dealings,
you know full well that all his
records were either seized by the police
or burned in the fire you started.
Pickens Park? More like Needle Park.
I wouldn't even go cruising here.
Hey, uh, feel free
to, you know, pitch in.
I get you're pretty much Beyoncé, but
today, you're just like us commoners.
I think your biceps
can handle it, Mantle.
- You trying to get me to flex?
- Josie.
You mind if I borrow Reggie
for a New York minute?
Please. Take him.
Love watching me walk away, huh?
What do you want, Veronica?
We were kind of in the
middle of something.
I want the name of your
jingle-jangle contact,
and I won't take no for an answer.
Betty, you have to talk to Jughead.
Soon, I promise.
I just need to take
care of a few things.
I'll go out on a limb and guess
you're Verne. You got my stuff?
- I don't take American Excess.
- Will this do?
My girl and I need a
reason to live tonight.
She broke up with her
beau. Full spiral. Tragic.
One fifty.
I know you're overcharging
me, but I'm desperate.
My compliments to the Sugarman.
Did I get it wrong? Isn't that the name
of the genius behind these sweet treats?
Have you ever met him?
What about my change, asshat?
Our Drugstore Cowboy
should be passing you
in three... two... one.
I've got eyes on him.
Me and my boy...
wanna challenge you to a race.
If we win...
Serpents remain autonomous...
and you quit dealing at Southside High.
And if we win?
We fold...
and you can continue polluting Southside
with your little straws of death.
So, the mighty Serpent Prince has
some stones, but not much else.
So, unless Your Highness wants to put
some of Daddy's territory on the table,
I got no reason to agree to a race.
They were following me.
Tried to get in the garage.
- Veronica?
- Betty?
- Archie?
- Jughead?
What are you doing here?
- Wait. So, these are your bitches?
- I beg your misogynistic pardon?
Why don't you take your skanks
and get the hell out of here?
Until you make me a better
offer, there'll be no race.
If you win... we'll
give you the Whyte Wyrm.
You can expand your
drug-dealing horizons
and upgrade out of
this literal hellhole.
We'll take the Wyrm and
Sunnyside Trailer Park.
Two turkey burgers and
a Cobb salad. To go.
Sharon.
Cheryl.
What are you still doing in town, Nick?
Picking up some fuel for the trip home.
How are you?
How am I?
You roofied me.
- You tried to rape me.
- I don't think that's what happened.
You're a Less Than Zero monster.
At least I'm not a desperate
tart from a truck-stop town, hon.
Let's not distort reality to
cover your morning-after shame.
You were high, half-naked
and begging for it.
Call your lawyer.
Seeing as you're such
an unrepentant spore,
I think I'll be pressing
charges after all.
Sweetie, did no one tell you about
the arrangement my parents made
with your cobra-like mother?
You're not gonna be saying
anything about that night to anyone.
After all, there's a reason
it's called hush money.
For the lady's meal, as well.
God bless Reggie Mantle
and his inferiority complex.
His car's a lot like him.
It's beautiful to look at...
but not much going on under the hood.
Um, crescent wrench, please.
Thank you.
So, this is what Serpents do for
fun, huh? Street-race rival gangs?
Just go ahead and say it, Betty.
You said you weren't
gonna join them, Jug.
And you said you loved me, and
then you dumped me via Archie.
Which, by the way, way
worse than via text.
I'm sorry, Jughead.
It won't make any sense...
but everything around us was
imploding, and I did it to protect you.
Betty, you did the one thing
that could actually hurt me.
I will explain everything
to you, Jug, I will.
But right now, I just wanna
get you through this race.
I had the most fascinating
chat with Nick today.
Then I went rummaging around
your bedroom until I found this.
Before you start casting
stones, you should kn...
The Lodges are still accepting
money from the St. Clairs
for their precious SoDale construction.
I don't care about them.
I care about my mother.
You defend Daddy even after
he murdered your son...
but you won't stand up for me.
Not even against my would-be rapist.
Oh, don't be absurd, Cheryl.
And give me that check.
Not until you tell me the
truth about the Sugarman.
He exists, Mother.
We both know it.
He worked with Daddy.
Your father...
Was an awful human being,
and thank God he's dead.
But I'm alive, and I'm begging you...
for once in your life,
be honest with me.
Care about me more.
It's simple.
The St. Clairs bought your silence.
But you're not getting
paid until I hear the truth.
What can I say...
or do...
to get you to stay here with me?
Instead of going to that dangerous...
dumb, possibly deadly street race?
Don't worry, Ronnie, I have a plan.
Like the plan you and Betty had when
you snuck into Ghoulie headquarters.
Touché.
One that hopefully keeps everyone alive.
Cheryl?
What? Slow down.
They what?
Are you still doing
business with the St. Clairs?
Letting them invest in
SoDale after what Nick did?
- To be fair, Cheryl's accusations...
- Cheryl's telling the truth.
I know, because Nick
tried to do it to me.
Nick St. Clair... hurt you?
Tried to.
But I stopped him before he got too far.
The next night, he went after Cheryl.
- Veronica, why didn't you say something?
- I didn't have any proof.
And Nick has done it
before, I'm sure of it.
Veronica, as God is my witness,
I swear to you, I will...
Under no circumstances will we
take a penny from that family.
All right, let's do this!
All right!
Not the kind of drag race I
ever imagined myself going to,
but at least the guys are hot.
Don't worry, Ronnie, we got this.
Just make it back to me.
Preferably in one piece, Archiekins.
Before you get in the
car, I need you to know...
I never stopped loving you, Jug.
I'm not sure I can.
Also remember, don't ride the clutch,
and don't let it slip between gear shifts.
You're an enigma, Cooper.
- Let's do it!
- Yeah!
Get these cars up in a row!
Race over Herk Harvey
Bridge to Dead Man's Curve.
First one back here wins.
- Uh, I usually do the honors.
- Not today, Cha-Cha.
I was born for this moment.
Engines warm and ready, gentlemen?
Whoo.
Damn it.
- Jug, we're coming up to the bridge.
- I know. I got this.
It's too narrow for both of us, Jughead.
Jug, we should abort.
- And let them win?
- We will both crash on that bridge.
Serpents are joining the Ghoulies
over my dead body, Archie.
I'm sorry, man, but I'm
not down for those terms.
Why would you do that?
Trust me, Jug, you're
gonna thank me for this.
Jug, stop! Jug! Jug!
Jug!
Come on, Jug, we gotta go. Come on.
Everyone scatter! The cops
are rounding up Ghoulies!
- Oh, my God, you're okay.
- We gotta get out of here.
- Come on, we gotta go. Right now.
- You called the cops?
You won't throw in with the
Ghoulies, but you will with cops?
- Where's the honor in that?
- Calm down, Tall Boy.
- You think I knew Keller would be there?
- I called Keller.
What the hell, Archie?
Did my dad tell you about this, too?
No, this was my idea to get
rid of the Ghoulies. It worked.
They get arrested for racing,
they're off the chessboard.
For how long? One month? Three months?
You know what they'll
want on the other side?
Your head on a stake! All of ours!
Careful you don't get burned again.
You said I never protected you.
The Sugarman...
was a story I concocted...
to turn an all-too-real monster
into a child's bogeyman.
And it worked, for a while.
But now I need the truth.
Over the years, there
were many Sugarmen...
each taking over for the last.
When Clifford decided
to groom your brother to take
over the family business...
he wanted him to meet
the current Sugarman.
I protested, but your father insisted...
and God help me...
so began the terrible series of
events that led to Jason's death.
Thank you for that, Mommy.
One more question: Who
is the sugarman right now?
Oh, my God, is that the Black Hood?
It's Cheryl.
Hey.
You did?
Who is he?
Wait, are you positive?
Betty?
Cheryl just told me the Sugarman's name.
Oh, my God, Cheryl
Bombshell for the win.
What do I do, Veronica?
If I give the Black Hood his name,
may God have mercy on the Sugarman.
And if I don't...
may God have mercy on all of us.
I assume my time's up?
Yes, Betty. Have you found him for me?
I did.
Good girl. Now tell me his name.
I could.
But that wouldn't do you any good now.
I've already notified
the sheriff's office.
You'll have to read
his name in the exposé
I just published in the Blue and Gold.
Care to comment?
I told you what would happen.
The Sugarman needed to be
brought to justice, not execution.
He will be dealt with in the right way.
You're playing a risky game.
Yeah...
but it's my game now.
Which is what, Betty?
A game that ends with me catching you.
I found out who killed Jason Blossom.
I found out who the Sugarman was.
You're next, Black Hood.
I'm breathing down your neck.
Can you feel it?
Can you feel me?
What are the other Serpents saying?
Some people give you props for
challenging the Ghoulies
and beating them.
Others hate that you
cut a deal with Keller
- because it puts us in bed with the pigs.
- I didn't. That was Archie.
Yeah, I know that and you know
that, but some of them don't.
No, is this another raid?
Didn't you hear?
They caught the Sugarman.
Did you hear about that teacher
at Southside High who got arrested?
Jughead was in one of his classes.
- How's he dealing?
- Honestly, Dad, I'm not sure.
I tried helping Jughead with something,
and it backfired.
He's pretty pissed off.
Well, it's not the
first fight you guys had.
Pretty sure it won't be the
last. You'll patch it up.
Are you okay, Dad?
Mm-hm. Yeah. Feeling better every day.
Lodge Residence.
I'm so sorry to hear that.
Of course, all our
prayers. Thank you, Andre.
Everything all right, mi vida?
The St. Clairs had a car accident.
They were run off the road.
Nick... he will recover, but
it's gonna take several months.
Oh, well.
Karma's a bitch.
Checkmate.
In the end, the girl
next door came clean
about her dance macabre
with the Black Hood.
Further confirmation that
everyone in Riverdale wears masks.
Case in point: Robert Phillips.
By day, he is a kind,
caring English lit teacher,
hiding his true identity,
a ruthless drug dealer.
Sweet dreams, Sugarman.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --