Previously on Riverdale...
How many times are we
gonna push each other away?
I know about the webcam-ing.
Can you show me how to do that?
Serpent law says you
can't hurt one of your own.
No! No!
How did the Uktena
evolve into the Serpents?
We didn't evolve, we were all
slaughtered by General Pickens.
You interviewed my grandfather
for a history report,
not some half-assed newspaper article.
I think we can all be
proud to live in a Riverdale
where young people stand up for justice.
Let me tell you something
about Veronica's parents
and the way they do business.
Isn't this something
the Serpents would do?
As long as you're dating Veronica,
I'm going to demand the best from you.
How would you like to
start your business tutelage
under my shepherding?
It's a classic trope of mob movies.
Rich, high-rolling gangster
takes small town kid
under his wing.
- Here you go, Archie.
- Thanks, Pop.
Small town kid
is ushered into an intoxicating
but dangerous life of crime.
No, Poppa, you don't need to travel
with your own chef,
we have excellent poutine
right here in Riverdale.
Because I've tasted it and it's superb.
Hey, run this to your dad's trailer?
And then pick up some loafers
I had resoled at the
Shoe Doctor on Main.
Happy to, Mr. Lodge.
- There he is.
- Sorry, Dad.
Sorry, guys. Mr. Lodge has
me running all over town.
Stick around. I've got the truck.
I'll give you a ride home.
I'm done here in 20 minutes.
I've got my bike.
And I still gotta pick up
his shoes, but I'll see you.
Ronnie...
That hem's high enough, Terry.
It's a confirmation, not a sock-hop.
Usually, it happens
when you're 12 or 13,
but my parents wanted
the same monsignor who baptized me.
Monsignor Murphy, he's
a friend of the family,
to confirm me, as well.
Wow, so this is a big deal, then?
It is. Especially to my mom and dad.
And, well, my whole family.
A lot of them are coming in for it.
So, do you have to... memorize stuff?
During the ceremony, Monsignor
will ask me to renounce Satan,
which, of course I will.
But otherwise, you mostly
do things in advance.
Like picking a sponsor.
I asked my abuelita.
And performing charitable works.
I'm volunteering at a soup kitchen,
if you'd care to join me.
There she is.
Let me take a look at you
My beautiful daughter, confirmed
in front of my family... Our family.
Oh, mija, you've made me the happiest
and the proudest father alive.
What do you think, Archie?
Isn't she a miracle?
She is.
She definitely is.
Sheriff Keller, what a surprise.
Jughead. FP.
Sorry to bother you. It's...
We don't have General Pickens' head,
and we do not know who stole it.
Same as the last four times
you came by to ask us and our neighbors.
You know, Sheriff, these visits
are starting to feel
a lot like harassment.
There's absolutely no evidence.
Zero proof whatsoever
pointing to any particular
group of suspects.
Well, you did write a
rather scathing article
about the General's legacy,
which prompted the
Southside Serpents to stop by
at Pickens' Day with an ax to grind.
I'm actually writing a new article
about how you seem to care more about
catching a vandal than the Black Hood.
Can I get a quote?
Do I look good?
- Mmm-hmm.
- Can I undress for you?
Yeah.
I love talking to you.
I like talking to you too.
- Can we meet sometime?
- Maybe.
Betty?
What's going on in there?
Why is the door locked?
You know how I feel about locked doors.
Yeah, you're the one who
likes to do the locking.
I heard voices. Who were you talking to?
Jughead. He had some
questions about homework.
Now can I finish
getting dressed, please?
Well, I...
I already invited Archie,
but I want you guys
to be there, as well.
Usually these kinds of events,
baptisms, confirmations
are family-only,
but since it's all about me
and you guys are my chosen family,
I pulled a few strings
and reserved you a pew.
What is the dress code?
Catholic chic. So, dresses
for the girls, veils optional.
And coats and ties for the boys.
Jughead Jones and Betty Cooper,
please report to the principal's office.
Jughead Jones and Betty Cooper
to the principal's office.
Since your article
attacking General Pickens
among others has come out,
it's been a steady stream of outrage.
Most recently,
Hiram Lodge's lawyer,
a Mr. Sowerberry has called
saying his client's considering
legal action against the Blue and Gold.
On what grounds?
Defamation of character, Mr. Jones.
Effective immediately,
you are both suspended
from the newspaper's staff.
You have the day to clean
out your personal things.
I'm so sorry, Betty.
I don't care if they harass me at home
or school, but you...
You don't deserve this heat.
Who's harassing you at home?
Sheriff Keller. He has no proof,
but he suspects one or
more of the Serpents,
probably me, decapitated the
statue of General Pickens.
And dd you?
Betty, how...
Why would I decapitate a bronze statue?
Maybe the same reason
you wrote that article.
To avenge Toni's grandfather.
I mean, you and Toni are close.
Sure.
- We're pals.
- Close pals.
I saw you guys at Pop's
early one morning,
in the middle of the Black Hood attacks.
You were having breakfast,
and you seemed like more than pals.
And I know it's not my place to ask,
but did anything ever
happen between you two?
Yeah.
The night of the Gauntlet,
after you sent Archie
to break up with me,
Toni stayed over.
She gave me a...
Tattoo.
And we did some stuff,
but not everything.
Uh-huh.
But since you brought it up,
have you done anything with
anyone since we broke up?
No.
Of course not.
Ooh-la-la!
- Is that for me?
- It is.
It's'confirmation present
from the St. Clairs, of all people.
Why would they think they
have the right to do that
after everything that
went down between us?
It's what families in our business do.
Even when we're at war, we give gifts.
To show respect.
Or, in this case, to
try and make amends.
Well, whatever it is, feel
free to burn or regift it.
Veronica...
Simone St. Clair called
to follow up on this gift.
She said that Archie paid
Nick an unfriendly visit.
Is that true?
Sorry to keep making you
double-check everything, Pop.
It's more to make sure I got it right.
Mr. Lodge's special orders
can get pretty complicated.
No problem, Archie.
After all, he's the boss.
What do you mean by that, Pop?
Crap!
You cannot just show up
at my house like this.
I haven't heard from you in a while.
I've been calling and texting.
There's been nothing to report.
You don't think your
girlfriend's confirmation
is worth a mention?
No, why would it be?
Our sources are telling us
Hiram Lodge's family is coming to it.
And by that, I mean his crime family.
I need you to be my eyes and
ears at that event, Archie.
What?
Is there a problem?
It's my girlfriend's confirmation.
It's a big deal to her.
I want to be there for
Veronica, not the FBI.
Unfortunately, Archie,
you'll have to be there for us both.
Sheriff Keller,
we have to stop meeting like this.
Where's your dad at?
Had a shift at Pop's. Why?
It's an eviction notice.
You, your dad, pretty much
everyone in this place,
you all got to clear out.
What?
Don't tell me this is
because of that statue?
For the millionth time, Sheriff,
we did not decapitate General Pickens.
And you can't use that
as some trumped-up excuse
to try and evict all of us.
Look, I'm just the messenger, all right?
This order comes down
from the mayor's Office.
Apparently, there's a lot
of back rent owed here.
You have 14 days to vacate.
Then perhaps while you're packing,
you might come across that head.
Calm the waters a little.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Sierra and Josie are here to...
Offer an apology after Pickens Day.
I had misgivings
about some of the decisions
your parents were making.
That was wrong and inappropriate.
Oh, these are stressful times, Sierra.
And neither Veronica
nor I hold any grudges.
Not at all.
In fact, I would love it
if you'd both come to my confirmation.
Veronica, Hermione, we
accept your invitation.
That makes giving you
your gift that much easier.
Josie?
If you'll have me,
I'd be honored to sing at
your confirmation, Veronica.
- No, you don't have to
- That's a lovely idea, Josie,
- we accept.
- But, Mom, I was gonna sing.
Or we could do a duet.
Do you know "Bitter Sweet Symphony"
from the Cruel Intentions soundtrack?
I can learn it.
We all got the eviction notices,
but I swear to you...
No one is goin' anywhere.
But the heat's been
on us since Pickens Day
and they're using that damn statue
as an excuse to turn it up.
But if we're gonna
fix this, I gotta ask:
Is anyone in this room responsible
for cutting off Pickens' head?
Why don't you ask your son
what he has to say?
What is your problem with me, Tall Boy?
You wrote the article
that started this mess.
You and your posse
fired the opening shot at Pickens Day.
It was a peaceful protest, Turncoat.
That accomplished nothing.
So what's to say that
you and your boyfriend
didn't go back that night
with a ladder and hacksaw
Hey! We didn't do it.
Hell, Tall Boy, you're the
tallest guy in this room.
You wouldn't even need a ladder.
Jughead... Tall Boy,
the last thing we need right now
is to turn on each other.
Hey... We'll find a way out of this.
I heard a rumor...
That you paid Nick St. Clair a visit.
And roughed him up a bit.
Uh...
The thing is, Mr. Lodge, I...
When I found out about what
Nick tried to do with Veronica,
I just... I got
so angry.
But still.
Beating up on a kid,
even a filthy animal like Nick St. Clair
while his legs are in casts...
I'm...
Impressed.
No.
I respect a man that
will go to such extremes
to send a message.
And I'm relieved that
Veronica has someone
so fiercely protective.
Of course, sir, always.
I have some out-of-town
guests coming in
for Veronica's confirmation.
I'm hosting a poker game
at Pop's the night before.
I'll need a couple extra hands to help.
Someone I can trust.
You know... To keep the drinks filled
and the cigars cut.
Are you interested?
Absolutely.
Sir, I'll be there.
Chic? Is that you?
Uh... Who are you? Where's Chic?
I'm Ben, Chic will be right down.
See ya.
Hey, what's going on?
I thought you had a job interview today.
I did. That was Ben.
He works concessions at the Bijou.
Pretty sure I got the job.
Well, I thought he might've
been one of your clients.
Never... I'd never tell
those guys where I live.
And don't you do it either, ever.
- I wouldn't.
- Good.
Boundaries are key.
They'll keep you alive.
This witch-hunt has to end, Mayor.
The Serpents had nothing
to do with that beheading.
You know that and in the meantime,
you're gonna tighten the screws,
you'll send Sheriff Keller
to sow seeds of unrest,
threaten to take our homes away?
Since when do you care about
the statue of a murderer?
Since Governor Dooley called
and read me the Riot Act.
That statue cost him a lot of money.
He's furious.
And you're supposed to
be an ally, Mayor McCoy.
So why are you doing
this? Unless it's...
Who's pulling your strings?
Is it Hiram Lodge?
You're a bright kid, Jughead.
I've always liked you.
So listen to what I'm telling you...
Back down!
What do you mean my dad
invited you to his poker game?
No, not to play, just to,
like, serve drinks and
bus tables and cut cigars.
- Whatever that means.
- But those games are private.
Daddy's inner-inner-circle.
Well, I guess I'm in.
Unless there's a reason
why I shouldn't go?
Come here. Excuse me.
This floating poker game is
a long-standing tradition.
It's been happening for decades.
It's incredibly high stakes,
in every sense of the word.
You're going to have
to be extremely careful
around these other players.
Okay? I just don't want you to get hurt.
Why would I get hurt?
I thought these guys were
close friends and relatives?
They are, but they're like Daddy.
They're old school.
Industry titans you don't want to cross.
Just promise me, you'll play it safe.
Ronnie, I'm refilling water glasses,
I don't think there's
anything to worry about.
Thank you for meeting with me.
You're the only person in this town
that I can talk to about
something like this.
Before you do, can I just
point out one thing?
I know what you're going to say.
Last time the Serpents
and I were in trouble,
I pushed you away.
What do you need, Jug?
Mayor McCoy thinks the
Serpents were the ones
who vandalized the
statue of General Pickens.
And now, suddenly, we have 14 days
to vacate Sunnyside Trailer Park.
What... That's illegal.
Technically, the trailer
park's on town property.
And not everyone has paid their rent.
Well, so, let's go talk to Mayor McCoy.
I did.
She's making this all
about the beheaded statue
and really it's just a pretense
to shut us up and get us out.
If the statue's what's fueling her fire,
then let's take away the gas.
"The Case of the Decapitated Statue."
Let's treat it like a
missing persons case.
Someone, somewhere,
must've seen something.
So, we'll canvas the
town with reward flyers
for anyone who has information.
Finding that head and who did it
would really take the wind
out of Mayor McCoy's sails.
So...
Find the head, save the trailer park.
You invited Archie to
work your Casino Royale?
Aren't you worried he's gonna find out
all our family secrets?
Business isn't discussed
when the family gathers
for such sacred celebrations
as your confirmation.
You always have an agenda, Daddy.
What is it this time?
After hearing about how Archie
took initiative with Nick St. Clair,
I wanted to see how he'd handle himself
in a room of my peers.
Yes, but why?
He's your boyfriend, mija.
And if this relationship
of yours persists,
at some point,
we may need to bring Archie in.
I thought outsiders weren't
brought in to the family.
Not traditionally, no.
But Archie, he may be more like
us than I gave him credit for.
No, he's not.
And I'm not sure I want him
to be... compromised.
I see.
But if things keep
going as they have been,
you're gonna have to make a decision.
Either we bring him in,
or he stays on the outside, forever.
All right, order of the Ophidians.
Jughead Jones.
Did you really think
you'd see the last of me?
What's the Snake Charmer doing here?
Dad?
No, I brought her in, to help us.
We don't need Penny's kind of help.
You don't get a say anymore.
Since you broke Serpent law
and hurt one of our own kind.
Penny was about to tell your dad.
Show him, Penny.
Show 'em all.
That used to be my Serpent tattoo,
until your son sliced
a chunk outta my arm
and left me bleeding
in a ditch in Greendale.
But I'm still willing
to help the Serpents.
Tall Boy showed me
those eviction notices.
They're legit.
Luckily, I can think of about
41 ways to stall the process.
And I'm talking years.
What's your price, Penny?
Blood for blood.
An eye for an eye.
I want back in with the Serpents
and I want him kicked out.
Oh, yeah, one last thing...
I want his tattoo carved off.
And I want to do it myself.
With a dirty knife.
Well? What did they say?
Are they kicking me out?
There's gonna be a vote.
You versus Penny.
Me versus...
What, they can't see what we get?
With Penny in the picture?
Penny's a cobra,
but mutilating her?
That's the kind of thing you
don't come back from, Jug.
Yeah, like stuffing a
teenager's body in a freezer?
You need to learn to
keep your damn mouth shut.
Tall Boy was right.
You brought the Northside down on us.
Serpents are losing their
dens because of what you wrote.
Don't kid yourself.
You're using my article.
And they're using what happened
to the statue of General Pickens
as an excuse to justify something
they've already been doing.
You think you're a hero, Jug?
Cutting up women?
Bringing the temple down
right on our damn heads?
You... will be the death of us.
Not the Northside, not Penny.
You.
Are you out of your freaking mind?
I'm not wearing a wire.
Archie, this poker game...
All the kingpins, together in one room.
We've never managed to
get anyone close enough
to them to hear and
record what they discuss.
Okay, hear, yes. Record, no.
You afraid we might capture something
that implicates your father?
Or Veronica?
I'm the one taking the risk here,
Agent Adams, not you.
We're doing this on my terms.
No wire.
I told you, Alice,
either Chic goes or I go.
Chic isn't hurting anyone.
And he just got a job.
Where was it, Betty?
- At the Bijou.
And he's offered to pay rent.
So, what's your beef with him?
He's a stranger, that's my beef.
So? Make an effort. Get to know him.
Yeah, please, Dad.
Can you just try?
Why don't you guys
call me when he's gone?
In the meantime,
I'll be at a ShareBNB
down by the Register.
Fine, Hal, do what you want.
Forgive me, Father, for I have sinned.
It's been some time
since my last confession.
The Bible says gossiping's a sin.
If that's true... Guilty.
Also, I admit to being, on occasion,
disrespectful to my parents.
But what I'm most worried about is...
That I'm doing something terrible
to a person I love.
Not only am I constantly lying to him...
Or, more accurately,
withholding the truth.
I fear I'm leading him
down an unrighteous path.
Monsignor,
as someone who's known my family
for longer than I've been alive,
I hope you understand my concern.
I do, my child.
And I pray you can offer some advice.
Ten Hail Marys, five Our Fathers.
Veronica,
how did your confession
with the Monsignor go?
To be honest, Tia,
I don't know if he gave
me much peace of mind.
Me, I go to Our Lady of Grace every day.
I light a candle and I put in
my requests to the Almighty.
Terry, how many glasses is that?
Requests for what?
For protection.
Our husbands? The risks they take.
Every day they come home in
one piece, it's a miracle.
Mmm. For me, I pray for forgiveness.
I have everything.
My husband... Your uncle,
he's good to me. And so I pray for him.
And for me. And for the kids.
And I also give to charities.
It helps me sleep at night.
You have to find your thing, Veronica.
I'm trying.
Was that your boyfriend who
came by the other day, Veronica?
- It was.
- Ah!
His name's Archie Andrews.
And do we know him? His family?
He's a local boy.
An, uh, inocente.
_
Full house,
aces over sixes.
You're on a lucky streak, Hiram.
That, or he's cheating us, Carl.
Kid's got hustle.
What's your name, Red?
- Archie Andrews.
- Archie, this is Lenny Kowalski.
Lenny runs canned meat out of Chicago.
They call me "The Butcher."
He's pulling your leg,
kid. No one calls him that.
Carl Martin, of Martin Brewery.
Finest beer in the Rust Belt.
I wouldn't say the finest.
And this charming
fellow is Poppa Poutine.
He owns a chain of hot
dog restaurants in Quebec,
which is why you never heard of him.
How's SoDale coming along there, Hiram?
Right on schedule?
Ah, no business talk, remember?
Hey, kid, what was your name again?
Archie. Archie Andrews.
Andrews, right.
Hiram... Doesn't your wife
know a guy named Andrews?
Yeah, she does.
Fred Andrews is one of
our business associates.
Was that your decision to
make him a partner... Or hers?
Smells delicious, Pop.
Don't get a chance to
make poutine very often.
I hope you enjoy it.
The hell is this?
Those aren't cheese curds!
I ordered poutine! This is vomit!
- You own this dump?
- No.
I own it.
Now apologize.
Apologize? For what?
For disrespecting Pop Tate.
I'm gonna go out and
get a little fresh air.
This place is a dive.
I'm sorry, Pop.
If you'll excuse my guest's
lack of social graces.
Toilet's clogged.
Enjoy your steak.
Ah, God.
Lodge is a problem.
Mmm-hmm.
He lost his mojo in the joint.
Went soft in the head and in the belly.
Others, back home, feel the same way.
Lodge is getting sloppy too.
And that whole St. Clair kid thing?
Exactly. Going after someone's
kid in such a blatant way?
Who does that?
Ah... And partnering up with the man
who's been messin'
around with your wife?
He's weak.
This is our chance, Lenny.
You think he should be removed?
Right after his daughter's confirmation.
I'll do it myself.
♪ 'Cause it's a bittersweet ♪
♪ Symphony this life ♪
♪ Trying to make ends meet ♪
♪ You're a slave to
the money Then you die ♪
♪ I'll take you down the only road ♪
♪ That I've ever been down ♪
♪ You know the one that
takes you to the places ♪
♪ Where all the veins meet Yeah ♪
♪ No change, I can't change ♪
♪ I can't change I can't change ♪
♪ But I'm here in my mold ♪
♪ I am here in my mold ♪
♪ But I'm a million
different people ♪
♪ From one day to the next ♪
♪ I can't change my mold ♪
♪ No, no, no, no, no, no ♪
Do you, Veronica Cecilia Lodge,
renounce Satan and all evil works?
And do you walk in
the light of the Lord?
I do.
What a beautiful service.
Sierra, how kind.
You can put that with
the rest of the gifts.
No, this one's for you.
The sale's been finalized.
You're now the proud owners
of what was previously Southside High.
Congratulations.
And to you, Madam Mayor.
Betty, you mind if I steal my man?
It's time for Archie
to meet my abuelita.
Of course. I'm gonna
go look for Jug, anyway.
Come on, Archie.
_
Hello, Abuelita. It's
an honor to meet you.
Ah. So handsome. Hello.
Ow.
Thank you.
Hey.
It's not like Jughead Jones
to neglect a free buffet.
You okay?
No, it's the Serpents.
They're meeting to decide if
I'm getting kicked out or not.
What, why are they doing that?
I broke a code, I messed up bad.
Really bad.
There's this person who suckered
me into delivering drugs.
And my dad, too,
he got roped in.
So, couple of Serpents and I, we...
Found her,
grabbed her,
and I cut her.
Cut her?
The worst part is,
none of it even matters.
'Cause she's back.
It's like every decision
I've made since we broke up,
including our break up, just
makes things worse and worse.
Hello.
Yes, it is.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're the ones who put up the flyers.
Okay, yeah. We can be right there.
Thanks for being here today.
I really needed to see your face.
You're my beacon in the night.
Hey, Archie, mind if I cut in?
No, sir, of course not, Mr. Lodge.
Daddy... I've been thinking.
I don't want Archie brought into this.
This life... Our life.
If that's the way you want it to be.
It is.
I think it has to be.
Okay.
You the kids looking for a head?
If only we lived in a town
where the answer could be no.
We are and you called
to say that you have it?
I got nearly ten acres
of scrap out there,
and I come across weird
stuff all the time.
But this is the first
time I found a bronze head.
It was stashed in an old refrigerator.
You didn't happen to
see who dumped this?
Has anyone suspicious been around here?
Well, I get scavengers all the time,
but there was a guy come in last week,
I'd never seen him before.
Claimed he wanted to
get some bike parts,
but he didn't buy anything.
Well, did you get his name?
What did he look like?
Low-life type.
Had on one of those jackets.
By any chance, was this gentleman tall?
Sure was.
I'm sorry, Mr. Lodge, can
I talk to you for a second?
Yeah, sure. What is it?
Not here. Your study.
Right now. It's important.
Okay. Let's go.
It's Poppa Poutine,
I overheard him at the poker game,
and I think he's planning something bad.
He said you were getting sloppy,
and that action needs to be taken.
I'm telling you, Mr. Lodge,
so you can protect yourself,
in case there's some kind of coup.
Thank you, Archie.
You can go back to the party
now. Check on my daughter.
Make sure she's having a good time.
Stop the damn vote.
What the hell were you doing
at the dump last week, Tall Boy?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm talkin' about you cutting
the head off the Pickens' statue
and stashing it at the dump
where you were seen, dumbass.
So start spilling!
Why'd you do it?
Someone put you up to this?
What's the Northsider doing here?
This is Serpent business,
it's on Serpent land.
She's here because she's one of us.
You haven't answered my son's question:
Why'd you do it?
'Cause I'm tired of seeing the Serpents
goin' soft under your rule.
Then Hiram Lodge came by,
wanting to stir up some trouble.
He said if I took the head,
he'd get McCoy and the
cops to swarm all over us,
'cause some chaos.
So Hiram Lodge
asked you to start a mutiny
and you helped him, why?
I figured it'd be my chance
to get rid of you, sunshine.
And if I got rid of him,
I could get rid of you, too, FP.
And then, what, you'd become leader?
He and Penny.
You're a Judas, Tall Boy,
and an idiot.
You betrayed your own kind, Tall Boy.
You broke Serpent Law.
What should we do with this lowlife?
Strip him of his jacket.
Exile him.
All those in favor.
Looks like this piece of trash and I
got a long ride ahead of us.
What were you and my
father chatting about?
We were just going over
some stuff for my internship.
Wait, that's still happening?
Yeah, why wouldn't it be?
I love you, Archie.
But we can't keep dating
unless you understand
something about my family.
About my father.
Look, I wanted to protect you from this,
but every day, you're getting
in deeper and deeper and...
The truth is, Archie...
My dad... He's...
- He's a...
- A mobster.
I know, Ronnie.
I've seen all those movies.
And the poker game last night.
Well, I mean, I wouldn't
put it so baldly.
But, Archie, it's not just what he is,
it's what he's planning to do.
In Riverdale.
SoDale is just the
beginning, it's actually...
- Stop.
- No, Archie.
- You need to know this.
- No, I don't want to know.
- Archie, he's going to...
- Veronica, I can't know.
I... I don't need to know.
Veronica, I love you.
And there's nothing you could ever say
that would change that.
Or make me regret being with you.
Or scare me away.
You don't have to protect
me from this, any of it.
I love you, Ronnie.
I'm with you.
Good ol' Hiram Lodge.
I wonder what he's planning for us.
And the Southside?
Maybe we can ask Veronica on Monday.
Yeah.
Maybe we should just investigate quietly
until we know more.
We haven't saved the trailer park yet.
And I'm on probation from the Serpents,
whatever that means.
Because of what I did to Penny.
But we stopped her from coming back.
And we got rid of Tall Boy.
We.
It's nice to hear that again.
Look, I'll be apologizing for it
for the rest of my life, but I'm sorry.
I am.
Feeling like I needed to shield you
from what I was going
through with the Serpents
or my darkness.
I can handle it.
I know.
I know you can.
I should probably
start headin' home.
Or you could stay.
Stay.
Wait, wait, wait.
- I need to tell you something.
- What?
What is it?
Nothing.
I just want you.
I want all of you tonight.
This is typical of your sister.
She gets caught up in something
and drops off the face of the Earth.
What about Hal? Where's he?
Hal...
That's probably him now.
Hi. Is Chic home?
What are you doing here, Agent Adams?
My dad's not even asleep yet.
This couldn't wait.
Paul Boucher was found
dead in his hotel room
less than an hour ago, shot
in the back of the head.
Who's Paul Boucher?
His mob name is Poppa Poutine.
This is extremely important, Archie.
Boucher was a guest at
Veronica's confirmation.
Did you see or hear something, anything,
that could implicate Hiram Lodge
in what is obviously a gangland slaying?
No.
Nothing.
Found one last gift for you
in the lobby, Miss Veronica.
A big one!
Mom...
Dad...
I think this might be for you.
Hello?
Mom?
Elizabeth, did you lock the front door?
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --