Previously on Riverdale...
I'm your uncle Claudius.
Daddy never said anything
about having a brother.
The Lodges. Have I dreamed
of getting my revenge on them.
Now, now, Claudius. First things first.
Nana, then Cheryl.
Effective immediately, Southside
High School is shut down!
Okay guys, let's not overreact.
Hiram is like Dracula.
He's snapping up properties
from all over Riverdale to
expand his empire and feed.
Twilight Drive-in,
Sunnyside Trailer Park,
Southside High and now,
Pops Chocolate Shop.
Southside High is
gonna be turned into...
A private for-profit prison.
We are leaving and we are leaving now!
Dad, I'm gonna stay.
It's tradition. It's been in my
family going back generations.
Now, Archie, we come first.
If it's the only way I
can get Chic to open up...
But catfishing him?
When you wouldn't
submit to the DNA test,
I found some of your dental
floss, and sent it to the lab.
You're not who you say you are, Chic.
One sheet of paper.
That's all it took.
To confirm everything
Betty had feared...
That she let a dangerous
stranger into her house.
This is why you didn't want
to take the DNA test, isn't it?
Because you knew what the
results were gonna say.
That you had no Blossom blood!
Of course I don't. I'm not a
Blossom. I don't even know them.
Blossom blood is Cooper blood, Chic.
My dad was a Blossom which means
you would have tested positively
for Blossom DNA, but you didn't,
because you're an impostor!
Mom!
Betty, listen.
The truth is Chic's DNA doesn't match
because Hal isn't his father.
But I am your mother, you understand me?
Hang on, what?
What? Then who is Chic's father?
Chic's my son!
And whoever the father is, is
not gonna be a part of our lives.
So there's no reason to open old
wounds that have healed many times over!
Come here.
Now, for our Register readers,
why would you, Hermione Lodge,
run for Mayor of Riverdale?
Every year, our population decreases.
More and more businesses
close. We're at a deficit.
We need to change that
equation before it's too late.
That is why Lodge
Industries has secured a bid
for a maximum security
prison on the Southside.
Now, that means jobs,
economic growth, stability.
It'll give Riverdale its future back.
You know, I have to ask.
You're building a prison
on the bones of a school.
Are you okay with that?
Losing a school is a
tough pill to swallow,
but once our correctional
facility is up and running,
a quarter of our earnings are gonna
be funneled directly into education.
We are building a brand
new wing at Riverdale High.
And Veronica, are you gonna
follow in your mother's footsteps
and run for Student Body
President in the upcoming election?
Maybe. If I don't have my hands
full, campaigning for my mom.
I'm excited to show Riverdale that
she's more than just a housewife.
And speaking of housewives...
We have a very special guest.
Bravo's very own Andy Cohen.
Mr. Cohen, what brings you to Riverdale?
I'm here to endorse my
great friend, Hermione Lodge.
She's a very savvy businesswoman.
She's always three steps
ahead of everyone around her.
She's a fighter too.
She doesn't give up.
I'll love to have her in my corner.
Kevin just died and
went to clubhouse heaven.
Thank you for letting
me invite him today, Mom.
Of course. Any and all good will
during this election will go a long way.
And, 'Ronica...
This campaign isn't gonna be easy.
Especially since we had to lead with
your father's plans for the prison.
Certain people in town and in
school are gonna see us as the enemy.
So after the celebrity endorsement,
let's keep our heads down
and let the storm pass.
- Understand?
- Color me a wallflower.
Dad, I know you think
a prison is a bad idea
for Riverdale, but Mr. and Mrs. Lodge
really have thought this through.
A prison would rip
the soul of this town,
especially the Southside, so
I'm not gonna support that plan.
Or Hiram and Hermione.
I'm severing all ties with
Lodge Industries and SoDale.
- All of it. I'm done.
- What? Just like that?
- Yeah.
- Will they even let you walk away?
I'm not asking his permission.
They will, or they'll have a
hell of a fight on their hands.
I just loved your spin piece
in the paper, Olivia Pope.
Can we not, Jughead?
Did you know about Southside
High closing? Or the prison?
Of course not. That was all
her parents' doing. Right, V?
She didn't know, Jughead,
okay? So, back off.
Fine. I have to conserve
my energy anyhow.
I'm going on a hunger strike
to protest Southside High
closing and to get it reopened.
What?
I'm sorry, man. It's just...
You're, like, always eating. I
mean, good luck with that, but...
Hey, it's Jughead's prerogative
to protest peacefully,
so we're gonna support that, aren't we?
- Veronica?
- Oh, hey, Ethel.
For your crimes against
the town of Riverdale,
for everything that you and your
family have done and continue to do,
we find you guilty.
Your sentence is this.
The chilling thing is
Ethel went through the trouble of
bringing that milkshake here from Pop's.
I mean, how mad is she?
My dad is responsible for the Muggs
family losing basically everything.
And he still hasn't made amends, so...
Ethel has a right to be upset.
So do you.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'll manage.
I'm impressed. I'd want
to rip Ethel's head off.
As my mom keeps saying,
this is not the time for drama
and flying off the handle.
I just need to...
Take deep breaths, keep
smiling, turn the other cheek.
Give Ethel a wide berth.
Veronica!
I heard you got a face full of dairy.
I've got some nuts to top
off that shake if you want.
Leave her alone, Reggie.
You do not want to push
me right now, Reggie.
One question I gotta ask, as
future Student Body President.
What are the odds your dad's the first
inmate in that prison he's building?
Oh, man... That's...
...for your mom.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Who's there?
Oh, don't be ridiculous, Cheryl.
No one was trying to break
into your room last night.
You're imagining things.
I swear, sometimes you're
worse than Nana Rose.
I know what I heard and saw.
Claudius, now that you're here,
we should talk about you taking over
Nana's stewardship of
the cereal business.
That factory is mine! I'm
not dead yet, you vultures!
Oh, Mother! Now, come, come,
come, let's not get too upset.
Have some more of Penelope's tea.
It's a special blend that she makes.
We're feeling a little
bit calmer this morning?
We are.
I'm drink my High Point Decaffeinated.
So you won't be punching a boy today?
Again, I'm sorry, Mom.
Maybe if you'd offered Mr.
Muggs a job at the prison,
all of this could have been avoided.
No, no, no. No, mija.
We tell you what to do.
And right now, we're
telling you again...
- Keep your head in the sand.
- Before it gets cut off.
We need you to be our
good, obedient little girl.
You can do that, right?
Friends, I have an exciting
announcement to make.
I'm running for Student
Council President
against Reggie "The Misogynist" Mantle.
You've got to be kidding me.
If yesterday's dramatic
events taught me anything,
it's that Veronica
Lodge is not a victim.
Nor will she ever
allow herself to be one.
Your parents are taking over Riverdale
and now you want to take over
our school? So what is this?
Part of Mommy and Daddy's evil bidding?
Jug, I get that you're in a bad
mood because you haven't eaten in...
Actually, Jughead, my parents
think I should avoid the spotlight.
- Really?
- But I was born for elected office.
V, if you want to be
President, you've got our vote.
Yeah, Team Ronnie all the way.
B? As the Thelma to my Louise,
I can't imagine doing
this with anyone else.
Will you be my running mate?
Of course, V. I'd be honored.
Amaze! B and V!
Now, that's a team you can believe in.
Well, I doubt there's any way
you amateurs are gonna top that.
So practice is over, Vixens.
Inner circle Vixens, hang
back. You know who you are.
In honor of Toni joining our
squad, I think we should celebrate
with a mandatory slumber
party at Thistlehouse.
Fancy dressing gowns are appreciated.
You've all seen The Beguiled, right?
Dinner at 8:00. Parlor games to follow.
And there's nothing I can
say to change your mind?
'Fraid not. I just want to get
out of this thing, Hermione.
As quickly, cleanly as I can.
You go about your
business, I go about mine.
I understand.
And I will talk to Hiram.
Of course, you know we'll need
to get our lawyers involved.
Yeah, yeah. I kind of figured that.
What can you tell me about
Jughead's hunger strike?
Yes, I heard about that.
Jughead loves a political crusade
almost as much as he does a burger.
From the contact we've had,
your friend seems to live
in a fantasy world of
ideals and theoreticals.
What if Southside High were to reopen?
I, on the otheothand,
live in the real world.
I see what needs to be done and I do it.
I think you do too, Archie.
I'm accelerating our timeline on
Southside High and I was wondering
if you could send Jughead a message.
Yeah, whatever you
need, Mr. Lodge, but...
But why you?
Well, I think it'll soften the blow
to hear it coming from a friend.
Hiram's trying to tear down Southside
High by the end of this week?
He's supposed to give the neighborhood
at least a six weeks' notice.
Who'd he pay off? Can I have
another water, please, Pop?
Thank you.
Jug, my dad got shot,
right here in Pops, because Riverdale
was sliding off the deep end.
And if Mr. Lodge's
plan can shore things up
and help make Riverdale more
secure for us and our families,
then I think that's a
good thing in my book.
Besides, why do you care so much?
You were only at Southside
High for like, four days!
You remember that I was
raised on the Southside, right?
My mom, my dad, Jellybean...
That neighborhood is the last
tangible piece I have of them
until your dad comes
in with his bulldozers.
My dad's actually
against this whole thing.
He's pulling out of his
deal with the Lodges over it.
You're choosing Hiram's side over his.
We see things differently,
okay? And it makes me sick.
Kind of like when you and
your best friend are two trains
running on the same track
in opposite directions,
destined to collide?
Inner circle, Cousin Betty?
I didn't just bring you to
Thistlehouse for a girls' slumber party.
The truth is I'm terrified
of being alone here.
There's a stranger in this house.
My uncle Claudius,
he's as mad as the sea,
and ever since he blew in, I
feel like I'm in mortal peril.
Wait, I'm confused. Is this
real or are we playing a game?
All too real, TT.
I feel like they're plotting
against me and Nana Rose.
Mumsy cultivates esoteric
herbs in the conservatory.
Tannis root, jimsonweed. I'm afraid
to eat for fear of being poisoned.
Cheryl, are you sure
you're not imagining things?
Well, if she is, Josie,
then maybe I am too.
There's a stranger in my life as well.
Chic. With him lurking behind
every corner, my house feels...
Dangerous. Deadly.
I sympathize.
Full disclosure...
I didn't want to invite
all the girls tonight.
But I knew my hideous mother would
never allow me to invite just you.
Which is...
what I craved.
A fall like that should have killed her.
- She's a lucky bird.
- Yes, that she is.
Poor thing loses her
senses at nightfall.
It's classic Sundowner's Syndrome.
Cheryl, what is it?
He's wearing my father's pajamas.
- What?
- My uncle.
Toni... I think they pushed
my nana down the stairs.
I think I'm next.
All this contract stuff with the Lodges.
Time to call in the big guns.
Now...
I wish you'd called me in earlier, Fred,
before you gave the Lodges
20% of Anderson Construction.
Mr. Lodge said he'll work
this out. He'll keep his word.
Yeah. Son...
Your mother and I have known the
Lodges a lot longer than you have.
- Meaning what, Dad?
- Archie!
It's okay. I better
get to school anyway.
I'm helping Veronica with her campaign.
Are we still on for lunch, Mom?
Hands where I can see them.
Here you go. Now remember,
vote Lodge-Cooper.
Okay, who's next?
The cupcakes have been flown in
from Magnolia Bakery in New York
but the kisses, however,
are locally sourced.
Uh, five minute hydration break.
Ethel, wait!
Sexualizing the election, Veronica?
Well, it might get you the boys,
but you can forget about the girls.
Right now, I'm only
interested in one girl. You.
Look, I know it's long overdue,
but I wanna make reparations.
So I'm working it out with my parents,
and you can tell your dad to expect
a great job offer very, very soon.
This isn't a demolition notice.
It's a notice of extermination.
We've already said our
goodbye to Southside, Jughead.
Today, it's Southside High.
Tomorrow, it's the world.
Everything that makes the Southside home
is gonna disappear.
If we roll over now, it's all over.
- It's just a building, Jug.
- No! Toni, it's the soul of the Southside.
They fought and died
trying to protect that land.
Our parents fought to keep
it safe during the riots.
Now it's our turn. It's our time.
This is our fight. So who's with me?
Who's ready to go to war?
Archie, I really hate to see
you and your father fighting.
We're not, Mom.
And look, you and Veronica,
it's your first real relationship...
I just wanna make sure
that you're not being...
led astray.
By Ronnie?
To align yourself with her family
against your better judgment.
It's not like that. Okay?
Veronica is an amazing person.
I'm sure she is.
But I guess I'm just
saying, so's your dad.
- Just...
- The best you can get.
Can't get any more...
What the hell's going on here?
Chic invited me over. Cookie?
No, thanks.
How do you guys even know each other?
It's a funny story.
Kevin and I have been
continuing our online chats.
Imagine my surprise
when he finally told me
it all started as a catfishing
scheme you cooked up.
- Kev, you sold me out.
- I felt bad.
Okay, Kev, you need to leave.
I need to talk to my
brother alone. Right now.
Betty, you're really
kicking me out, right now?
- Mmm-hmm.
- It's okay, Kev. I'll catch you later.
Do not mess with my friends.
Mess with?
What do you think I'm doing here, Betty?
Clearly, there's something you want.
Some void you're looking to fill here.
Like brother, like sister, right?
"We share the same darkness."
Isn't that what you said?
Yeah, I guess I was wrong.
You know nothing about my darkness.
But you will.
Josie? Look, I know things haven't
been smooth sailing between us.
Are we even on speaking terms, Veronica?
I mean, you did steal
the Pussycats from me.
Borrowed them after you dumped them.
What do you want, Veronica?
A celebrity endorsement for my campaign.
Yours. And before you say no...
Andy Cohen is a very old,
very good friend of the family.
Okay, my ears are perked
Because I never miss an episode
of Watch What Happens: Live.
- How would you like to be on it?
- What?
- As a special guest.
- Okay, if you can make that happen...
Consider yourself endorsed.
Amazing.
My point is, Hermione, some may
read this document as exploitative.
Come on now, Mary. Now, that's not fair.
Look, fair would be an immediate and
compensated release from the contract.
How does that sound, everyone?
Oh, sorry. It keeps buzzing.
Hiram here.
They're doing what?
Mr. Lodge?
What?
Yeah, don't worry. I'm on it.
Well, well, well. The
cavalry's finally here.
Guess that means we've
got Hiram's attention.
Are you nuts?
Chaining yourself to this place?
They're gonna tear it
down in two days, dude.
Not unless Hiram wants the blood of
eight young Serpents on his hands.
We're not going anywhere.
Go and tell your boss we said that.
Hello, brother.
Betty, what...
You think you're the only one who
can scare people by being crazy?
You may have fooled
my mother, but not me.
I'm gonna bring you down.
Because I catch bad men.
I caught Clifford Blossom.
I caught the Sugarman.
I caught the Black Hood.
And you know what they all
have in common? They're dead.
Consider yourself warned.
God, why didn't you
call me last night, Jug?
I would have brought you
and your crew blankets.
You would have tried to stay the night.
Are you sure you're
not gonna get arrested
for trespassing or
protesting without a permit?
Oh, that's the beauty
of all this, Betty.
See, if Sheriff Keller and his goons
try and manhandle a bunch of teens
peacefully trying to save their former
school, it's just gonna look ugly.
Not to mention, probably
go viral, which...
at this point, it is
publicity I would welcome.
Also, no one's gonna mess
with those guys over there.
Good point.
I have some Student Council
obligations with Veronica,
but I'll be back later tonight, okay?
Go get 'em, Tracy Flick.
We live in uncertain times,
but here's one thing
I'm very certain of...
My girl Ronnie here, along with
her running mate, Betty Cooper,
has my vote to be Riverdale High's
next President and Vice President.
And of course, we remind
everyone, especially the women,
to vote and be heard this election.
♪ Now, you have heard
of women's rights ♪
♪ And how we've tried
to reach new heights ♪
♪ If we're all created
equal, that's us too ♪
♪ Well, sure, some men bowed
down and called us Mrs ♪
♪ Let us hang the wash
out and wash the dishes ♪
♪ But when the time rolled
around to elect a president ♪
♪ What did they say, sister ♪
♪ Oh, we were suffering
until suffrage ♪
♪ Not a woman here could
vote, no matter what age ♪
♪ Then the 19th Amendment struck
down that restrictive rule, yeah ♪
Okay, what's going on?
- Where did you get all this information?
- Does it matter?
It's the truth, isn't it?
I don't understand.
I told you that we were making amends,
that your dad would get a job offer.
You mean, your half-hearted bribe?
Yeah. Too little, too late.
B, wait!
This is insane.
- Thanks for the intel, Josie.
- No problem.
The Lodges hurt a lot
of people this year.
Your family, my family...
We girls, we gotta to stick together.
That day in the student lounge
when Weatherbee announced that
Southside High was closing,
you acted like you didn't know.
When my parents asked me to help them,
I didn't feel like I could say no.
Of course you could've.
You could've told your parents that you
didn't want to be their teen accomplice,
or you could have told us the truth.
Instead, you just played us like fools!
No, I was just trying
to keep them honest!
That's why I started working with
them. Betty, you have to believe me.
Even if I dil I can't be your running
mate anymore. You know that, right?
I can't trust you, V.
Veronica...
Rough day on the campaign trail?
- How did you find out about that?
- Weatherbee called.
He also read me the flyer
that's been going around school.
Now do you see why we asked
you to keep a low profile?
And instead, you're running for
Student Council President. Why?
Because, Mom...
I'm out there every day, facing what you
and Daddy have done, what we've done.
And maybe, if I'm their President,
people at school like Ethel
Muggs or Jughead or even Betty
will stop looking at me
like I'm just the daughter of
criminals, like I'm a criminal too.
We're out there
fighting a holy war, Mom.
I need something I can use as a shield
against everything
that's coming our way.
Protection from everybody
out there who hates us,
who's out for our blood.
Stop right there, young
lady. Come in here now!
Is it true that you snuck into
your brother's room last night
to torment him with a Zippo lighter?
And what exactly is this for?
Oh, my God, you creep! What did you
do, go through my dresser drawers?
I was looking for the lighter as
proof and found all your secret toys.
Why, in God's name, do
you have this cabaret wig?
She wears it when she
has sex with Jughead!
Is that true, Elizabeth?
I...
How would you even know that?
- I was guessing.
- Guessing?
Betty, what... Is it,
is it true? Are you...
Are you and Jughead...
Yeah, Mom. We are.
Last man standing.
What happened to no Serpent left behind?
Ah, they were claimed by frostbite.
They'll be back after some
coffee. They'll warm up.
Too bad. I got a dozen burgers.
Guess they're all yours now.
Come on, boy. It's just you and me.
I'm not gonna tell anyone
you broke your hunger strike.
So, uh...
Just like clockwork, I
got a call from Hiram.
What's he offering this time?
You know how they're saying SoDale
will mostly be low income housing?
Well, apparently, there'll be
a few penthouses at the top.
Would be more than enough space for
all of us. Your mom, Jellybean...
Just like you always wanted.
Just imagine me,
standing on that balcony
and looking over a prison...
Right in the same spot that all my
friends and I used to go to school.
And Jellybean, growing
up in a town where...
Best hope, or only
hope aside from getting
the hell out, is to work at the prison?
It's not right.
What'd you say to him?
Nothing. I hung up on his ass and
went to Pop's and got some burgers.
I was hoping to see
Jughead while I was in town.
He's still at Southside High,
Mom, chained up like a lunatic.
Arch, you might not believe
in what he's fighting for...
I'm not sure he's
fighting for anything, Dad.
I think he's mostly
fighting against Mr. Lodge.
Like a lot of people in
this town who are afraid.
- Archie!
- Afraid? Afraid of what?
Afraid of having a vision, of
seeing what has to done and doing it.
I hope that you're not
referring to your father, Archie.
This man who broke rocks
when he was in high school,
to support his family
when his dad was sick.
A man who saw what had
to be done and did it.
And built a business out of nothing.
One that pays for this house
and the food you eat every day.
And for your information, your father
had and has a vision for Riverdale.
One that doesn't, thank God, end up
with everyone working in a penal colony.
Now, you don't have to
side with your dad, okay?
You can side with Hiram Lodge,
even though he's a crook,
and has no intention of letting your
father out of that contract, by the way.
You can do that. That is
your right. But I'll be damned
if I'm gonna sit here and
listen to you disrespect him!
Betty, I have to ask...
Are you being safe with Jughead?
Yes, Mom. Of course.
Well, that's something.
Because look, when I was
your age, I wasn't always.
But you need to be, and
I am very well acquainted
with how alluring the Jones men are.
Whoa. Wait, Mom...
Did you and FP...
I mean, is it possible
that FP is Chic's dad?
Absolutely not.
But Chic is a part of our family.
He's your brother. I
know that he's odd...
and damaged. I see that, I'm not blind.
But for the past 25 years,
he hasn't had anyone to love him.
He's dangerous.
Mom, don't forget what he did.
I will never forget, Betty.
But Chic needs us.
Dr. Masters?
Any updates on my nana?
Yes, we just got her panel back.
There was a trace amount of a
paralytic toxin in her bloodstream.
Tannis root, which is
strange because it's so rare.
But as your mother
and uncle explained it,
they've caught your Nana
on more than one occasion
chewing bits of tannis root
she grows in your greenhouse.
So, it's more of her
Sundowner's Syndrome.
We'll keep her for
observation another day,
then she should be well
enough to return home.
To my mother and uncle? No, Dr.
Masters, you don't understand...
Cheryl! There you are.
Looking a little worse for wear.
Poor dear, hasn't slept in days.
Why don't we stop bothering Dr. Masters
and I'll take you straight home?
Come on.
Mom says we should bury the hatchet.
So for her sake, how about a truce?
Why should I believe you when all
you've done is try to get rid of me?
If I really wanted to
get rid of you, Chic,
I would go down to the Sheriff's
office and explain to him
how you brained a man in our kitchen.
You're not gonna do that.
You see, I never
touched that body, Betty.
Or the car. Or went through his phone,
or called his contacts. I
didn't go to the sewer pipe.
It's not my fingerprints
or hair they're gonna find.
You know, maybe I
should call the police,
tell them what sort of things
my sister's capable of doing.
You wouldn't dare.
You know, I don't think I'm
comfortable being in the same room
as someone who's done
those sorts of things.
It scares me, Betty.
You scare me. Can't you see that?
You're scaring me,
Betty. You're scaring me!
I think I figured it out.
You paralyzed Nana Rose
with the tannis root.
And then pushed her down the stairs.
You've gone mad.
That's all there is to it.
You have lost your mind
and you leave us no choice.
What do you mean, no choice?
But it's all right.
We're gonna make you all better.
All better.
Every hour that passes
that Jughead is out there
is bad for business.
It's time to remove Jughead and
his fellow Serpents by force.
Grown-ups going after teenagers?
Wouldn't that be bad for business?
If Sheriff Keller and
his men do it, yes.
But boys, led bravely by you?
The wrestling team. No one
would be too upset by that.
I can't.
I'm sorry. I won't.
Archie, you made a promise to me.
An oath to this family
in this very room.
If you break it, there
will be consequences.
I understand.
So you'll help me?
Yes, sir.
But I hope you can prove
your loyalty to me in return.
Hmm. And how would I do that?
By releasing my dad from all
commitments to Lodge Industries.
Save our school! Save our school!
Cops may let you by, Red,
but you come in here acting like a
big man and I will knock you down.
Dad, don't! They'll throw you in
jail. Don't give him an excuse.
I'm sorry, Jughead.
Me too.
I'm not gonna fight you, Archie.
Look around.
It may have taken a couple of days,
but now people know what Hiram's doing,
what's happening here.
This fight is not gonna go
away. We're not gonna go away.
So go on, cut us down.
I want them to see you do it.
You think it even made any difference?
- Us freezing our asses off?
- Definitely.
Every revolution starts somewhere.
Good.
'Cause I've been thinking,
we lost Southside High.
I don't want to lose Riverdale High too.
And you've not heard more unlikely
words come from my mouth, Betty, but...
I wanna run for Student Body President.
And I want you to be my co-president.
- I know that you and Veronica...
- Okay.
Really?
- Just like that?
- Just like that.
I'm in, Jug.
There is no me and Veronica.
You have to do me a favor, though.
You have to let me stay here.
I can't stay in the same
house as Chic anymore.
Okay.
What's going on?
Your pal Hiram Lodge called.
He's letting your dad
out of his contract.
Well, I never doubted
your mom for a second.
- I knew she'd do it.
- Wow. That's...
That's great.
Yeah, and another thing, son, your
mother and I have been talking, and...
I'm gonna stick around for a while,
help your dad with some
more unfinished business.
That contract was the last
thing holding him back.
From what?
I'm gonna run for Mayor.
Against the Lodges, come what may.
Mrs. Blossom, hi.
I'm looking for Cheryl. She wasn't
at the hospital with her nana.
No, she's gone.
Boarding school in Switzerland.
All girls. She left just last night.
Mrs. Blossom, that
doesn't make any sense.
Don't come here again.
Oh, honey. Poor child.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Sister Woodhouse is going to help you.
Thank you, Sister Woodhouse.
Yeah, she's gonngo rid you
of all those naughty demons.
The ones making you think
such awful, unnatural thoughts.
Today, you must rest.
Tomorrow...
The real work. The conversion begins.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --