Previously on Riverdale:
Bringing the Southside
under control is my priority as mayor.
If it means arresting every single
Serpent in sight, so be it.
How many times will we
push each other away?
Until it sticks.
- You tried to rape me.
- You won't say anything to anyone.
- There's a reason it's called hush money.
- Thank you for that, Mommy.
Cheryl is telling the truth.
- Nick tried to do it to me.
- Nick St. Clair hurt you?
- The St. Claire had a car accident.
- Karma's a bitch.
This is where we end this
and stop the Black Hood.
- But right now I need you with me.
- Archie.
I love you, too, Archie Andrews.
Know how there are some towns
where bad things always seem to happen?
Well, Riverdale has become
one of those towns.
The most recent horror?
The school janitor turned out
to be a serial killer.
But we were putting him away
along with our Christmas decorations.
Now we were back to your
typical small-town intrigues.
Clandestine meetings behind
closed doors and the like.
Yes, by and large, it was
business as usual in Riverdale.
Good news, Cheryl.
I've earned nearly enough
to pay for that tree
and those ludicrous presents
you bought yourself.
Bravo.
Never mind that the last two weeks,
I've been living in a bordello with a...
woman of the night.
Well, it's not that different
from when I was younger
and I had my pick of gentlemen callers
lining up every evening.
Good God,
you almost sound proud.
You wanted me to get a job,
Cheryl, and I did.
Providing comfort and companionship
to the lonely men of Riverdale.
- Veronica, have a minute?
- Just checking in.
See how you're feeling.
Ah. Checking to make sure
I'm on board with the "plan"?
Don't worry, I am.
- You're gonna be at ground zero.
- The eye of the potential hurricane.
You said that when
I wanted to shop in SoHo
during Occupy Wall Street,
and I was fine.
- Uh...
- Dad, Mom, trust me.
I'll keep my classmates from revolting.
And they'll be none the wiser.
Hey, Arch, did you say anything
to anybody about my medical bill?
Because it's been paid, all $86,000 of it.
Something called an angel donation.
No. Well, I mean, Veronica,
but she wouldn't...
- I'll ask her.
- No.
I'll get to the bottom of it.
You just focus on school.
- Haven't seen that guitar for a while.
- Yeah, well, I've been busy.
I spent break writing songs.
I'll start a band like the Fred Heads.
If you do,
do that in the garage.
That's why
I soundproofed it for you.
- Ronnie.
- Hey.
Hey, did you tell anyone
about my dad's hospital bill?
Hmm. Did I?
I may have mentioned it
to my mom and dad in passing.
- Ronnie...
- They wanted to help.
And they have
the means to help.
What, is your dad upset?
Are you?
Upset?
Ronnie...  I am crazy about you.
Students of
Riverdale High, this is your principal.
E-mails have been sent to your parents,
but effective immediately,
Southside High School
is shut down.
Its students will be transferred
to other schools in the district,
including this one.
I believe the statement
we're releasing
- Guys, let's not overreact.
- Will address your concerns.
You should receive it shortly.
- I'm sure you have many questions.
- Like "what the hell?"
It goes without saying,
we are welcoming these students
with open minds, hearts and arms.
- Cheryl?
- Hell, no.
My home life is
a Dickensian nightmare.
- I won't have school turn into one, too.
- This won't affect course schedules
or locker assignments.
Thank you.
That is all.
Wait, what does that mean?
- It means Jughead's coming back.
- Betty, are you ready for that?
Of course.
We're fine.
- But why is this happening now?
- Who knows?
It's probably some bizarre,
byzantine town ordinance
we couldn't possibly understand.
In the meantime, let's receive the exiles
as if they were our own flesh and blood.
Who's in? Hmm?
Wow, Jones, props to you.
It's very Lovecraftian.
Which I'm sure was
the intention.
But did you write
this on a typewriter?
Yeah, I wanted to
get into Lovecraft's headspace.
So, it wasn't like Betty bought you
a typewriter for Christmas or anything?
No comment.
What's going on?
This hellhole's officially closed.
No more Southside High.
What? How?
It's gonna be quarantined.
We're going to different schools.
This doesn't make sense.
Where are you guys going?
Same as you, and you, and Fangs.
We're going to Riverdale High.
Think of all those
Northside heads to knock.
Thank you, Principal Weatherbee.
Keep me posted.
Well, it's done.
Any minute my phone will start exploding
with calls from outraged parents.
It'll be news for two days. Look how
people stopped talking about Black Hood.
After a few weeks,
we'll quietly go about purchasing
the land beneath Southside High.
And you, Madam Mayor,
will get your commission.
A sizable donation
to your re-election campaign.
Mom? Dad?
All right, whoever you are...
Betty, don't shoot.
It's just me.
Oh, my God. Polly, I almost pepper-sprayed you.
What are you doing home?
- I just came to get a few things.
- Oh, my God. What happened to the twins?
- I had them, Betty.
- You did?
You didn't call us.
Mom will be crushed that she wasn't there.
- We have to call her.
- No, Betty, we don't.
Leaders of the Farm think
it's best if I sever all ties.
The leaders of the Farm.
You mean the cult that you joined.
It's not a cult. And on the Farm,
there's no stigma on my babies.
- You can tell Mom and Dad.
- Tell them what?
I don't know anything.
Do they have names?
Juniper and Dagwood.
Oh, my God.
Polly, please, okay?
Mom and Dad hurt you, yes,
but what you're doing right now is
cruel, and selfish, and vindictive.
I'm really sorry,
Betty, but I gotta go.
That's mine, by the way. The Farm probably
doesn't have electricity, anyway.
Archie Andrews?
I'm Special Agent Adams
with the FBI.
Hi.
Can we take a walk?
I always loved this park.
Came here every weekend.
Played ball with my dad,
ran around with my dog.
- You're from Riverdale?
- I am. Born and raised.
- That's why I was assigned this case.
- What case? Why do you need to talk to me?
How well do you know
Hiram Lodge?
I date his daughter.
We believe Hiram Lodge is conducting
criminal activity here in Riverdale
with ties to organized crime.
Between your relationship and your
father's connections to Lodge Industries,
you're in a unique position to help us
take him down once and for all.
- Mr. Lodge is a businessman.
- Let's talk about that.
A few months ago, one of Hiram's
business associates came
to visit with his family.
The St. Claire.
They were going to invest
in Hiram's SoDale project,
but for whatever reason,
the deal fell through.
The St. Claire went back to New York,
and their son, Nicholas,
was soon admitted to Columbia-Presbyterian
with life-threatening injuries.
- You think Mr. Lodge is responsible?
- We do.
- Veronica is my girlfriend.
- And her father
is an extremely dangerous man.
- He's hurt people, maybe worse.
- What do you expect?
Find out what happened to
Nick St. Clair.
The truth.
- Based on how you do on that assignment...
- I have not agreed to anything.
Anyway, is this even legal,
what you're asking me to do?
- Don't you have to talk to my dad?
- He's in business with Lodge.
For all we know, he's part of
Hiram's criminal activities.
- Get real, my dad is not a part of this.
- We don't know that, not for sure.
Maybe if you helped us,
we could be more certain.
Look, I know it's
a lot to take in.
Think about it and call me.
Well, that is one
mystery solved.
- What?
- Hiram and Hermione paid my hospital bill.
- Dad, you can't accept that money.
- I already did.
Traded 20 percent of Andrews Construction
to cover the 86 grand. A good deal.
What? Dad, no.
I can't take out another
mortgage on the house.
Lodges will let me buy
it back in pieces.
But that just puts us
in deeper with them.
They just bailed me out of a jam.
What's the problem?
Mayor McCoy's obviously hiding
something about this Southside debacle.
- Sorry, what?
- Schools don't just close overnight.
- Mom, Polly...
- Oh. Have you talked to her?
I've left messages to make sure
she has everything she needs
and ask what color she wants the nursery.
- I was wondering if you'd heard from her.
- No, not in a while.
"Mayor McCoy has deemed Southside High
a public health hazard
due to toxic fumes from
the methamphetamine lab in the basement."
There was no meth,
just Jingle-Jangle.
So, the worm turns,
and it's back to Riverdale High, huh?
- Something smells fishy.
- Damn straight, something smells fishy.
The real reason
you don't wanna go back.
What do you mean?
Oh, she just walked
through the door.
Thanks for
meeting with me.
Yeah, no problem.
I was gonna reach out
and clear the air
before Dr. Beaker awkwardly
pairs us up in chemistry or something.
Actually, I wanted to meet
because I need help.
You remember that baby
my mom put up for adoption?
Long lost Cooper sibling?
Yeah.
I was hoping you'd put me
in touch with your social worker
to see if she can
help me find him.
Betty, of course I'll help,
but why the sudden need for a brother?
Polly had the twins.
She didn't even call
my mom to tell her.
I know my mom's crazy,
but she's also... really sad.
So, maybe if she found her son,
having him in our lives...
- I'll send you Ms. Weiss' number.
- Thank you, Jug.
As for clearing the air, I'm happy
you'll be back at Riverdale High.
- Thank you for inviting me up.
- There's always room at our table.
I wanted to say thanks
for helping my dad.
- We were happy to.
- He'd do the same.
In return though,
I've put together a welcoming committee
for tomorrow's arrivals,
and I'm hoping
you'll stand by my side, Archie.
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
Uh, Mr. and Mrs. Lodge,
what about Southside High closing?
It's close to the SoDale project.
Isn't that bad for business?
Drugs, gangs and violence.
That's bad for business, Archie.
Mm.
So, investors like
the St. Claire are fine with it?
Archie, um,
the St. Claire aren't investors anymore.
Oh.
- Not after what Nick did to Cheryl.
- What happened? Did he get charged?
We severed ties with the St. Claire.
Don't think we called after the accident.
Accident?
Nick St. Clair had an accident driving,
um, in Vail.
Or was it on the slopes?
You know, I'm not sure.
Is he...?
Is he okay?
Well, you know,
from all reports,
he's recovered enough to be back at, uh...
Was it Greenwich Prep?
- Yep.
- And may we never hear from him again.
Mm.
Friends. On behalf of the students
and faculty here at Riverdale High,
welcome to your new school.
To ease this transition,
they've set up a registration desk
where you can get locker assignments,
schedules and a list of extracurriculars.
We encourage every one of you
to drink deeply from the cup
that is fair Riverdale.
Stand down, Eva Peron.
There's the school spirit
I so fondly remember.
Cheryl, no one invited
Fascist Barbie to the party.
Wrong, Veronica. No one invited
Southside scum to our school.
Listen up, ragamuffins.
I will not allow
Riverdale High's GPA to suffer
because of classrooms overcrowded
with underachievers.
So, please, find some other school
to debase with your hardscrabble ways.
Why don't you come over here
and say that to my face?
- Happily, Queen of the Buskers.
- Okay, guys. Everyone.
Can we put our Northside-Southside
differences apart and start over?
- A new slate?
- You don't speak for the Bulldogs.
I remind you, these greaser-snakes
showed up at your place to kick your ass.
Time to finish
what we started.
I am so over the toxic masculinity
in this hallway right now.
All right, enough pomp
and circumstance.
Everyone, let's get to class.
Now.
You traitors picked
the wrong side.
Nice to see you with Veronica.
Especially considering
that clandestine Christmas kiss
between you and Betty Cooper.
Care to reconsider
your allegiance?
Cheryl.
I was unsurprised and pleased to get your
text suggesting this meeting, Archie.
I'll keep it brief.
If you don't convince Veronica
to stand against the Southside rabble,
I'll tell her
I saw you kissing Betty Cooper.
We were broken up,
and so were Jughead and Betty.
That's not why I texted you.
Oh, Archie, do you really think
you're going to outmaneuver me?
I want to talk about Nick.
What on earth for?
Did you know that after he left,
he got into an accident?
- Like, a pretty bad car crash?
- Forgive me if I don't shed any tears.
I only wish Mother and I
hadn't burned the check he gave us.
You must've been thrilled, too,
when you found out.
After what Nick did to Veronica
at his party.
- What?
- When he got physical.
- What do you mean?
- I mean, if Veronica hadn't slapped him,
the same thing that happened to me
might have happened to her.
- I am going to murder him.
- Archie...
I genuinely thought you knew.
It was Veronica's right
to tell you or not.
I'm sure there's a reason
she kept it from you.
Yeah, and I think
I know what it is.
As is typical, your brother's files
were made public when he turned 18.
His name is Charles Smith.
After your mother gave birth,
he entered, and stayed in,
the foster system.
- You mean he wasn't adopted?
- Unfortunately, no.
The last address we have for him
is two towns over, in Centerville.
I don't think we've properly met.
Veronica Lodge.
Of the Park Avenue Lodges.
Toni Topaz.
Oh, like the purple-colored gemstone.
Love it.
And I'm Josie McCoy,
formerly of the Pussycats.
Now just Josie.
And this is Kevin.
- What's your name?
- Fogarty. Or you can call me Fangs.
- Your last name's Keller, right?
- How did you know that?
Joaquin and I used to hang out.
He talked about you all the time.
You guys. Yes, you.
Come with me.
Now.
Which of you defaced our school
seal with this graffiti?
This is what they do,
Principal Weatherbee. They tag their turf.
Reggie, could you be
any more transparent?
Effective immediately:
No gang behavior of any kind
will be tolerated in my school.
As of this moment,
no more Serpent jackets.
- What?
- You're kidding.
No more Serpent jackets.
All tattoos are gonna be covered.
Possession of any gang paraphernalia
will lead to immediate suspension.
Are we clear?
That's all.
Mom. Dad.
Polly had the twins.
- What?
- I don't understand.
- She...
- I do. I understand.
She didn't... Doesn't want us
to be a part of the babies' lives.
Isn't that right, Betty?
Well, are they healthy?
Is Polly all right?
Yeah. She is. And they are.
Good.
There's something else.
I did some digging,
and I found an address...
for your son,
my brother.
- His name's Charles...
- Betty, what are you talking about?
What? I thought it might help,
now that Polly's...
No.
This has nothing to do with Polly or you.
- Okay, Hal...
- I did it for Mom, Dad.
Mom?
Your father's right.
Okay.
I can't believe
you guys don't see it.
Weatherbee is profiling us.
Telling us what to wear. What's next?
Brain implants controlling what we think?
You sound like a conspiracy nut.
- A school closed down.
- A crappy school.
Now we're at a better one,
with a computer lab and textbooks.
And toilets that flush.
Getting transferred to
Riverdale High is the best thing.
Maybe ever.
If I have to take off my jacket 8:30 to 3,
Monday to Friday, hey, I'm down with that.
My dad soundproofed this,
so I could practice.
Get back to it when this is over.
- Said you had something for me?
- Yeah.
Nick was hurt badly in
some accident in Vail,
according to the Lodges.
- But it may not be an accident.
- What?
Before I say anything else,
I need assurance from you...
that no matter what happens to Mr. Lodge,
my dad is not gonna go to jail.
I can protect your father.
Nick assaulted Veronica.
- If Mr. Lodge found out...
- It'd give him a motive.
Can you get confirmation
from his daughter?
No way, I'm not using Veronica.
But I might be able to get to Nick.
Smart.
He's more likely to talk to you than me.
But what if he tells Veronica
I was asking about the accident?
Or tells his parents
and they tell Mr. Lodge?
You need a Trojan horse.
A cover story. A reason to see Nick
that has nothing to do with the Lodges.
- Can you think of anything?
- Maybe, yeah.
What do you want?
I can't stop thinking about what
Nick did to Veronica. And to you.
Do you want another
check from Nick?
I mean, of course I'd take it, but...
I'm afraid the ship's sailed on that one.
Really? Because I was thinking of
going to see Nick.
I could ask him for you,
and I bet he'd give it to me.
I need to borrow
one of Jason's blazers.
Mom?
We can't tell your father,
because he wouldn't support it...
but I want to see him, Betty.
I want to see my son.
Oh, hey, guys.
What's up?
Take it off.
Take off that jacket, rat boy.
Oh, Reggie, I don't think you know
what this jacket means.
Because you have no sense of honor,
or history or loyalty.
That's it.
- Get him.
- Do it.
Oh, my God.
Mr. Weatherbee.
You all have detention
for fighting.
But I made myself clear
to you, Mr. Jones.
Take off that jacket,
or you're suspended.
- Please, Jughead, just...
- I guess I'm suspended.
Weatherbee told McCoy, who told us,
integration is not going well.
Reggie's just being Reggie,
but he has made gang-wear a flashpoint.
The Southsiders need to
start looking the part.
So, I propose a charitable donation,
to help out the fashionably misguided.
Hi.
Forty dollars a night for a single bed,
20 for a bunk.
Oh, we're actually looking for someone.
His name's Charles Smith. Do you know him?
237.
It's okay, Mom.
Come in.
Charles? Charles.
My name's Alice Cooper.
This is my daughter, Betty.
- We're... I'm...
- I know who you are.
The sisters gave me your address
when I turned 18.
When they kicked me out.
I even went by your house.
A nice place to grow up.
You didn't want to come in?
Meet us?
You probably didn't want
somebody like me around.
- That's not true.
- You're my sister.
- Yeah. Yes.
- You're lucky she wanted to keep you.
- Charles, I...
- It's Chic.
But how would you know that?
You know what? Forget it.
Go. I have a client on the way.
- What work do you do?
- For real?
Fantasy fulfillment.
Now, really. Go.
Come on, Mom.
You break that, you buy it.
- How'd you know I was here?
- Hog Eye called.
- What's up, Hog Eye?
- FP.
Explain why you're not in school.
Yes. Weatherbee has been
disrespecting the Serpents.
He's been targeting us.
He told us to take off our skins.
You mean your jackets?
Wear them after school.
- A Serpent never sheds his skin.
- I know the laws, boy.
What's going on, Jug?
Really?
At Southside High, we had a place.
Yeah, it was crappy,
but it was ours.
We were a family.
We had a home.
I had a home.
Yeah, I hear you.
But getting arrested for truancy's
not gonna help. Be smart.
Serpents hibernate
during the winter.
Look at me. Think I like cleaning toilets?
Shoveling slop? No.
But it's what I gotta do.
Going to Riverdale High,
that's what you gotta do.
So, lay low for a while,
but you never stop being a Serpent.
Hey, Nick.
Nice dorm room.
What are you doing here?
And why are you wearing that blazer?
You remember Cheryl Blossom?
You wrote her a check covering damages.
Well, that check got lost.
So, you're gonna write it again.
Right now.
For double.
That's it? Money?
Checkbook's in the desk.
You got hurt bad.
How'd that happen?
- Ski accident.
- Ski accident?
Wow. You must really suck at skiing. So,
you wiped out and snapped both your legs?
Yeah, I wiped out on the slopes.
What the hell do you care?
I don't care. I'm just curious.
It's weird. You come to Riverdale,
act like a jackass, try to rape Cheryl,
blow up some deal between the Lodges
and your folks, and skip back to Vail?
For some little ski weekend?
I don't know, that seems weird.
You're not here for Cheryl.
Yes, I am.
I'm here to get what you owe her,
you scumbag.
I don't even remember
you being friends with Cheryl.
- Probably because you were high, Nick.
- Why are you really here?
For Ronnie?
Payback for what you did to Cheryl...
and Veronica.
Payback? No.
No, you know what I think?
I think you're a small-town hick
who's realizing how deep
into shark-infested waters he really is.
Careful. When Veronica Lodge smells blood,
she'll turn on you, too.
What the hell? Guys?
Weatherbee gave them to us.
Said he understood that not
every Southside student
had the means to purchase
Riverdale High-acceptable clothes.
He thinks this will
help us fit in.
- Where's Fogarty?
- He wouldn't wear it.
So, they suspended him.
So our choices are
conform or be cast out.
Yeah.
"FYI, your insane boyfriend
just ambushed me in my dorm room.
He broke my nose and
was foaming at the mouth.
- Hope you've had your shots."
- I can explain that.
By all means, Archie, I would love to hear
why you went to New York behind my back
and attacked Nick St. Clair.
I wanted to beat him after what
he did to you after that party.
Who told you about that?
The only people that know
- are me, Nick, and...
- I did.
I told him. I told Archie the truth
about that staph-infection for a human.
And I convinced him
to pay Nick a visit.
- Cheryl, why would you do that?
- Classic shakedown.
I wanted money. Archie convinced
Nick reparations were in order.
My only regret is that I betrayed
your confidence, Veronica.
And for that, I'm sorry.
Hey...
I'm sorry, too.
I should've told you.
Hey.
Let go of him.
I said, let go of my brother.
Come on.
Something's off with you.
Huh?
Call it girlfriend's intuition,
but you're hiding something.
I wanted revenge
for what Nick did to you...
That's true, okay?
I swear.
- But there is one thing I left out.
- I knew it.
What?
The reason I visited Nick
in the first place...
Cheryl was blackmailing me.
Pardonne-moi, blackmailing you?
- How?
- On the night of the Black Hood...
Cheryl saw...
Cheryl saw me and Betty kiss.
What?
When, why and how?
It was after you dumped me.
Jughead dumped Betty.
Nana Rose told this story about
Betty's grandfather. It happened.
You and Betty... kissed?
It was that crazy night, Ronnie.
Literally 40 minutes later,
the Black Hood was burying me alive.
You and Betty... kissed.
We haven't talked about it since.
I don't think we'll ever talk about it.
It's okay.
Do you know why?
Because I believe you.
You're being honest with me.
That's more important than a single...
"my life is in danger" kiss.
I love you, Ronnie.
I love you, too.
Mom? Dad?
I need help.
Betty, what happened?
Welcome to the inaugural meeting
of the Swords and Serpents Club.
- Which is what, exactly?
- Like I told Fogarty to lure him back...
We are a gaming group,
sanctioned by Mr. Weatherbee, himself.
Where like-minded
students can meet
and concoct world-building,
role-playing scenarios,
inhabiting fantastical heroes
and dispatching mythological creatures.
No, but really.
It's a club.
For us.
A safe haven where we can be Serpents,
in school hours, under everyone's noses.
We won't shed our skins.
We're lying low,
in the tall grass.
I've solved all our
problems, Mommy.
Blood money from the St. Claire.
And this time,
you have my blessing to deposit it
in a bank, not in the fireplace.
Aren't you glad?
Your days of being a courtesan are over.
Mommy, I said you can stop.
Oh, but Cheryl...
Now, why would I stop...
when I'm having
such a good time?
I know there's a lot to discuss
and sort out.
But for now, try to
get some rest, okay?
Good night, Alice.
- Good night, Hal.
- Good night, Chic.
You'll be safe here.
Why didn't you say anything...
about what happened with you and Nick?
I felt foolish.
For not seeing him for
what he really was.
Did you tell anyone
besides Cheryl?
Kevin, but that's it.
I asked for
protection for my father.
I want it for Veronica, too.
I don't want her hurt or in trouble.
Help us, and she
and your father are both off-limits.
- Protected.
- I want that in writing.
Absolutely.
You can't get emotional again,
like you did with Nick.
- You get emotional, you get sloppy.
- One more thing.
If you've followed me around,
you must know about the Black Hood.
I do. Nice job.
In your expert opinion, Agent Adams,
do you think we got the right guy?
I haven't told anyone
about this...
but I'm not so sure we did.
And so, Archie,
always trying to do the good, noble thing,
took another step
further into darkness.
And Betty, the girl next door,
had no sooner vanquished
one monster...
than she'd perhaps let another one
into her family's lives.