Previously on Riverdale
We will not rest
until those responsible
For the murder of our sister
is rightly punished.
Fangs...
Mrs. Klump, the Sheriff's department
is working around the clock...
you were supposed to be
protecting our children.
What's all this?
It's ransom money.
Not for Archie, I got him back.
This is from when I turned the tables on
Nick, and held him for ransom instead.
I still haven't made my bones with you.
There's only one man I'm interested
in bringing down, the Black Hood.
And whatever I can do to help you
on your quest, you can count on me.
This is the Black Hood speaking.
I got a letter. These symbols
look so familiar to me.
I used to check out
this book obsessively.
Betty, how could
the Black Hood know that?
Put it on.
Why are you doing this to me?
To show you that we're the same.
Where is he, Betty?
Where did you take Chic?
Did you kill my brother?
I didn't mean to hurt him.
I'm gonna give you a head start.
Mom, where's dad?
Hello.
Hello, Sir.
I'm campaigning for my dad, Fred Andrews.
He's running for mayor of Riverdale
and could really use your vote.
On the Eve of
the mayoral debate,
As Archie Andrews
goes door-to-door,
He doesn't mention the murder
of his classmate, Midge Klump.
Excuse me, Sir.
I'm campaigning for my dad, Fred Andrews.
I'm voting for Hiram Lodge.
Don't you mean Hermione lodge?
Take the flyer, Sir,
in case you change your mind.
Sure.
Most people believed Midge
was murdered by someone else
But not Archie.
He was certain,
beyond a shadow of a doubt,
The Black Hood was back,
As was his next-door neighbor,
Betty Cooper.
Who had, in fact,
laid eyes on the Black Hood
And suspected he was much closer.
Penny for your thoughts, hon?
I was thinking that he was a test.
Who was?
The impostor, Chic.
Everything that he did to us
and brought to us,
Was kind of a test.
But we survived
and we're stronger for it.
Well, that remains to be seen.
No, mom, we are.
And we'll survive
whatever else comes next.
You can't see
my bruises anymore.
Yes, no reason
whatsoever to bring up
Nick's failed attempt to kidnap
and murder you.
Speaking of, there is one
thing I wanted to tell you.
What's that?
Word of my exploits serving
Nick his comeuppance
Has seeped into the demimonde
of mobsters and molls
My father used to associate with,
So the five families are sending
their youngest and brightest
Their "princes," as it were
to, well, come court
the rare mafia princess
Who can belly up to the bar
with the big boys.
What do you mean, "court"?
Thanks to my play, the families
are looking to make a business
And/or political alliances
with my parents.
It's all very Borgia-Medici.
Archie, if you have a moment?
Go ahead.
We'll meet up at lunch,
After I welcome the tributes.
My spies tell me you're out
campaigning for your father.
I'm not campaigning, Mr. Lodge.
I'm trying to find
the Black Hood.
It sounds insane,
but I remember his eyes.
So I'm going house-to-house to...
Stare into men's eyes?
Well, that sounds like
looking for a needle in a haystack,
But we don't even know if that
the needle is in the haystack.
You said you wanted to make your bones.
Is that still true?
Yes.
Well, then...
Why don't you reform
your Dark Circle?
You'll want back-up should
you identify the Black Hood.
Reggie and the guys are
fired-up, Mr. Lodge, for sure,
But I need focused lasers,
not loose cannons.
To help with that...
A new Sheriff's taken over
for Keller, Michael Minetta.
A man I know very well. You could
coordinate your efforts with him.
Really?
Yes.
I'll arrange a meeting.
But move fast, Archie.
Every hour that passes, our killer
could be planning his next attack.
Any word from Chic?
No. He hasn't called since
I took him to the bus station.
So who knows?
Maybe he's gone for good.
Hey, the silver lining to all this Chic
stuff over the last couple of weeks is...
That's as bad as it gets, Betty.
It can't get worse, how could it?
My dad could be the Black Hood.
Yeah, okay.
Well, that would be worse.
Well, well, well...
Aren't you boys a handsome
assortment of he-devils?
Veronica, these young men have
come to pay their respects.
Oh, I know why they're here, mom.
And while I'm dying to hear proposals,
I'm already late for school.
But maybe I can squeeze you in tomorrow?
Uh... Tomorrow?
You do things your way,
mom, I do things mine.
There's no one else
that I can talk to.
No one else who might understand
what I'm going through.
Dear cousin, you look harrowed.
What is it?
Cheryl, before you saw
the video of your dad...
Shooting Jason...
Did you know that
he was the murderer?
Subconsciously, yes.
Why do you ask?
I think there's a chance that my dad...
That somehow...
He might be the Black Hood.
Oh. Oh, Betty, I don't know.
I've seen your pater
sneak around Thistlehouse,
And he has all the stealth
of a marshmallow man.
Wherefore comes this accusation?
It's just intuition.
Cheryl, I don't want my dad
to be a murderer.
It would destroy our lives even more,
But I don't know...
I can feel it in my bones...
If you're coming to me for advice, fine.
Let's get you to the Po-Po.
Maybe this new Sheriff
has half a brain...
No. No. Not Yet.
I need to be sure before
I involve anyone else.
Also, I know
it's hard to explain,
But if my dad is the Black Hood,
I need to be the one who
confronts him, who stops him.
In that case,
absorb my hard-learned advice.
You need concrete proof,
or a confession, or both.
First step? Buy yourself time
while you investigate.
That means pretending
everything is normal.
Yeah, well, luckily,
that's my specialty.
You're playing a very
dangerous game, Betty Cooper.
I don't think he would hurt
his own daughter.
And I never thought my dad would
shoot his son in the forehead,
But that's the world we live in.
Tread carefully, cousin.
You and Fred are neck-and-neck,
And with the town divided over
our prison, this debate is...
Is the single most important
event of the election.
I know.
I know, basta.
We already control the Sheriff's
office, and the register,
But we need the mayor's office as
well, so the prison can't be blocked.
I'm hoping Archie's Dark Circle
will cause unrest.
After all, if Fred can't control
his own son,
He certainly can't control a town
on the verge of sliding into chaos.
If what happened to Midge
taught us anything,
It's that no one is safe, anywhere.
This town needs us,
it needs the Dark Circle.
And this time, we'll have
the new Sheriff's support.
No offense, Kev.
None taken.
Here to catch the guy
who cost my dad his job.
Guys, I...
I gotta tell you something.
The night of the show, Midge and I got
into a fight backstage cause she admitted,
She was seeing someone else,
behind my back.
Who?
She let it slip that
it was a Serpent.
What?
I knew it, I knew it, the second
they set foot in this school!
Moose, why didn't you say anything to us?
Or my dad?
I didn't want to look like the jealous
boyfriend and have people think that I...
We should talk to the new Sheriff...
screw that!
Some Serpent scumbag was doing Midge.
We just gotta figure out which one.
War baby called my father
and I from Shankshaw.
Her old adversaries,
the Ghoulies, had been released.
Word on the street is that
they want Serpent blood.
They're gunning for a re-match.
They want war.
Which one of you reptiles
was screwing Midge Klump?
What the hell is going on?
This is a private meeting.
I'm guessing it was you, Sweet Pea.
Reggie, that's enough.
You ass, I didn't even know Midge.
But yeah, I get why she wouldn't
want fleas from you mangy bulldogs!
Reggie, no!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Stop fighting now!
Synced & corrected by MaxPayne
== https://subscene.com ==
So I've been thinking.
Dad, you've been so busy
at the register lately.
Maybe mom should go back to work.
I mean, she's moderating the debate,
why not report on it, as well?
I suppose it's not a terrible idea.
Yeah, and I could help, too, after
school with proofing and layout.
My two best girls back at the register?
It's bad, Jones.
It's really bad.
So talk to me, Fangs.
On the opening night of Carrie,
when you were backstage
Filming your documentary and you
found me in Midge's dressing room...
I wasn't just giving her notes...
You were hooking up.
And you didn't tell Sheriff Keller?
Jeez, Fangs, do you know how
guilty this makes you look?
I know! I know.
Did you do it?
Of course not.
You've got to believe me, Jones!
I do!
Can you delete the footage
off your camera?
I already gave the footage over
to Sheriff Keller as evidence.
What do I do, Jones?
Nothing.
Lay low.
Serpents got your back.
I got your back.
Okay.
Canned meat isn't exactly sexy,
but it's making a comeback.
Tell your folks
we should open a cannery
In that maple syrup factory
I saw on the river.
I only like my meat
free-range and grass-fed.
My family runs a five thousand-seat
arena in pacific city.
They're looking to do the same here.
Do you have a favorite boxer?
Michelle Rodriguez girlfight.
My family owns a track.
If you get your old man to invest with
my old man, I'll name a horse after you.
I want ships named after me, not horses.
We own and operate the largest chain
of casinos in the region, Ms. Lodge.
And we're looking to expand.
I'm not opposed to games of luck, Elio.
But are your dice loaded?
No. No need to be crooked.
Or haven't you heard?
The house always wins.
Tell me more, Elio.
And it's Veronica, not "Ms. Lodge."
this is some pretty
forceful branding, Archie.
Reggie made those, not me.
I need your Dark Circle
to just lay off my Serpents.
Even though they were technically
right about something.
What do you mean?
One of my Serpents was
canoodling with Midge.
But he didn't kill her.
And I'm not gonna give you his
name so please don't ask.
But rest assured, none of my crew is a
middle-aged white guy with green eyes.
And that's who you're still
looking for, right? Yeah.
I'll tell Reggie to lay off.
Thank you.
In the meantime,
I need to get back some possibly
Incriminating footage
from this new Sheriff.
Have you met him yet?
No. But do you mind if I tag along?
Gentlemen...
This is the young man I was
telling you about, Archie Andrews.
The one organizing the safety initiative.
The Dark Circle.
A man after my own heart.
And this is the other one...
The muckraker.
The trouble maker.
You forgot iconoclast.
I was wondering if I could
have a word about
Some documentary footage
that I lent your predecessor?
Sure. Let's chat in my office.
Hmm. Archie, Archie,
Archie, Archie...
You said you wanted to introduce
me to Sheriff Minetta, Mr. Lodge,
So I took it upon myself to stop by.
Well, since you have
so much free time,
Veronica may have mentioned
that she's entertaining
A young man from
a prominent family tonight.
I'm hoping that
you'll accompany them?
Absolutely, Mr. Lodge.
Out of all the offers on the table,
Elio, yours inspired me the most.
So what if our families were to partner
up for say, "The Sweetwater Casino"?
Nothing would make
my father happier.
Perfection.
Now, play nice, boys,
while I go powder my nose.
How'd you get in with the Lodges?
I'm mostly just with Veronica.
My dad says
you're one of Hiram's capos,
That you made your bones
taking care of Papa Poutine?
No, that wasn't me.
Word is, Papa Poutine's son,
Small Fry is looking for payback.
No one in Riverdale
had anything to do with that.
You sure you don't want to take
a break and join us for dinner, honey?
I'm not hungry right now. Will you get
me a tomato bisque for later though?
Okay. And maybe, an orange freeze?
Sounds great, dad.
I got into my dad's planner.
And cross-referenced the dates
Of every Black Hood attack with
his schedule, and they all line up.
Okay. "Worked late" the night
Midge and moose were attacked.
"Early meeting"
the morning Fred was shot.
"Business trip" the night
Ms. Grundy was killed.
Business trip to Greendale, no doubt.
This isn't proof,
but this is corroboration.
Register.
Mrs. Cooper, this is Dr. Curdle
from the coroner's office.
How...
How can I help you?
I have a warm body for you.
Unidentified male, mid-20s.
His body turned up off the highway,
just outside town, mutilated.
Mrs. Cooper.
Are you there?
Yes.
Yes, I'll come... I'll come by to see it.
Thank you, Dr. Curdle.
As always, small bills are preferable.
We have to go to the morgue.
Why?
Another Black Hood victim?
I sent the Black Hood after Chic.
I gave Chic a head start and told him
to run, but maybe he didn't make it.
Sheriff Minetta wouldn't
give me back my footage.
Says he wants to go
through it frame by frame.
It's only a matter of time before he puts
two and two together and brings Fangs in.
Damn it.
Of all the girls in Riverdale high...
what do I do?
If Fangs runs, he looks guilty.
If he's caught withholding the truth,
he'll look like the killer.
It's a perfect storm.
The Lodges endorsed
this new Sheriff.
They want Midge's killer caught
And if it's a southsider,
so much the better.
Then we hunker down...
get ready to fight.
Dad?
What are you still doing up?
I got this note.
Pinned to the front door.
I can only assume it's from
our old pal, the Black Hood.
It's clear what has to be done.
We cancel the debate.
Prank or not,
it's not a risk we can take.
I agree. Until the Black Hood's
caught, we have to be careful.
Can you beef up security
at the town hall?
Fred, honestly...
dad, you can't be serious.
We'll lock town hall down
tighter than a steel drum.
The town is scared. They need
to be shown we can't be cowed.
Well, if Fred's in, so are we.
You're not the Mrs. Cooper
I was expecting.
Yeah, well.
My money's good just the same.
This poor creature was found in the men's
room at the rest stop outside of Greendale.
Betty, it's okay, it wasn't Chic.
But it could have been.
Chic is probably out there, with
a bullet in his forehead or...
Or he got away, and he's on
a train back to Transylvania.
I delivered him to the Black Hood, Cheryl.
That makes me a murderer.
I've been trying to prove
that my dad's a killer,
When really, all I have to do
was look in the mirror.
Oh, God!
He got what he wanted.
We're the same.
None of this is your fault, Betty.
Part of me wanted to punish
Chic for what he did.
If Chic is dead,
that's a psycho's doing, not yours.
I don't know how much longer
I can keep going
Before I snap and say something.
I think you should say something.
I think you need to confront your father
With as much of the truth as you dare,
And see how he reacts.
I have something to confess.
Well, what is it, honey?
While the Black Hood
was first hurting people...
He was also calling me,
Asking me to do things.
He said I was like him.
He offered to help me get rid of Chic.
So I delivered Chic to the Black Hood.
If he's dead,
That makes me
an accomplice to murder.
And I think...
I'm okay with that.
The truth is, there's always been
this darkness inside of me...
I thought Chic could help me
understand it, but really...
It was the Black Hood who did.
Honey...
I don't know what to say.
Betty...
I experience it, too,
The darkness.
When I was away from you and your mom,
I felt like I was drowning in it...
It's why we need each other.
Jug, did you see it?
See what?
Fangs was dating Midge and
didn't tell Sheriff Keller.
Where'd you get that video?
It was posted on the register's
website, somebody leaked it.
It makes Fangs look guilty as sin.
Attention, students.
This is principal Weatherbee.
I need Fangs Fogarty to come
to my office immediately.
Where is he?
I don't know.
We have to find him
before the Dark Circle does.
What the hell?
That video's everywhere!
How did it get out?
We have to get you out of here, all right?
You're dead, ViXen killer!
This way...
Mr. Fogarty!
We need you to come with us.
I didn't do anything.
Okay, okay. Come on, come on.
Hey, hey!
I know today is all about the
debate, but I was curious.
Did you get my proposal?
About partnering with Elio's
family on a modestly-sized casino?
I did, yes.
But no business
Elio's family runs is legal.
Their casinos are just fronts for
numerous criminal activities.
No, no, daddy,
Elio assured me...
This partnership
just doesn't make sense for us.
Not now, not when we're on the
verge of coming out of the shadows
And into the light, ourselves.
Surely, you understand that?
You don't have to do that.
There's a deputy out there.
What if the deputy falls asleep?
And the Black Hood slips past him?
What if I can't stop him again?
Again?
Look, Archie, what happened at pop's...
changed everything, dad.
I really thought you were
going to die, dad. I felt...
Helpless.
Everything broke that day, and I've been
trying to put it back together ever since.
First with the red circle and then...
Hiram Lodge.
Is that what this is about?
You backing him? Working for him?
He makes you feel...
I just hate feeling like
I can't do anything.
I know you do, son.
Especially when it seems like
the whole world is on fire.
All right, war dogs.
Let's have some fun.
Whoo!
Jug, what's up?
You and your Dark Circle went wilding on the
Southside last night, that's what's up!
Wait, hold on.
That... That's impossible.
Unless it was some other vigilante
group in letterman jackets
Who set a dumpster on fire
and slashed our tires!
Archie, hog eye saw you guys!
Jug, I swear, I don't know
anything about this.
I wasn't there.
Jughead?
Attorney McCoy.
Where is he?
You were in Midge Klump's dressing
room doing what, exactly?
We were just talking.
I didn't kill her.
Didn't you? With this knife
you had on your person?
Don't say another word.
I'll be representing Mr. Fogarty
from here on out
And I'd appreciate it,
if you'd stop harassing my client.
You're being held because you were in
possession of a weapon on school property.
My switch-blade's for protection.
Yes.
Well, they have 24 hours
to make something stick.
In the meantime, you exercise your
right to remain the hell silent.
Have you guys lost your minds?
Vandalizing the southside?
We were celebrating Fangs' arrest.
That's not something to celebrate,
you idiot! He didn't do it.
Archie, he had a knife on him.
Okay, we're not having
this argument, you guys.
The circle is officially disbanded.
That's not your decision to make, dude.
You're not the one paying us.
Hiram is.
Wait...
Mr. Lodge is paying you?
Yeah.
He's the one that suggested
we go out and have a little fun.
Said you might've started the
Dark Circle, but it was mine now.
Veronica,
I'm afraid I've already taken
On my pro Bono case
for the week.
That should cover an hour
of legal advice, I hope.
What can I do for you?
Let's say someone wanted
to open a casino in Riverdale.
For starters,
they'd need a gaming license.
Which are difficult to obtain without...
Connections.
Let's say one wanted to do this,
strictly above board.
Has he confessed yet?
No.
But he said something about not being his
best self when my mom kicked him out.
And it was just a hunch, but I got
into his credit card statements
And he's still making weekly
payments to the sharebnb
He'd been renting
even though he's back at home.
Do you think
it's his serial killer lair?
And please tell me
we're breaking in.
What are we looking for, exactly?
Trophies from his victims?
Or just anything unusual
or incriminating.
Hmm.
Betty?
Does your father have
an affinity for kiddie lit,
Or would this be considered unusual?
Cheryl...
The Black Hood used this book
to write the cipher,
The cipher that only I could solve.
My dad knew I was obsessed with
this book, growing up.
Oh, my God! It's him.
Don't answer it.
Hi, dad.
Betty, where are you?
Um, I'm at Pop's with Cheryl.
Well, your mom and I are
about to head to the debate.
You want us to wait?
Or pick you up?
No, just go ahead.
We'll meet you there.
Daddy, I've done a little research,
and I've figured out how
We can make the casino happen
without involving Elio's family.
And it's legal, like you asked.
I didn't ask.
And we're moments away from your mother's
debate, so if can we table this?
Welcome, one and all,
to tonight's mayoral debate.
Jumping right in.
Fear and unrest rule the streets.
Hermione Lodge, how would you
restore safety to the town?
Well, we're already
making strides, Alice.
My husband and I personally recruited
Sheriff Minetta from Centerville
after Tom Keller resigned.
Not one week on the job, and he's
apprehended Midge Klump's murderer.
Fred? Rebuttal?
We don't know if he's the killer.
All I'm saying is let's not call
for blood until we've had a trial.
What does that say about us,
about Riverdale?
You talk about not calling for blood, Fred?
Are you aware of a group
called the Dark Circle?
No, I'm not.
Then let me enlighten you.
The Dark Circle is
a dangerous, radical group
That traffics in terror,
violence and street-warfare.
It's a group...
Started by your son, Archie.
Now I ask you,
citizens of Riverdale...
How can we trust
a man to run a town
When he can't even keep
his own house in order?
Oh, my God!
It's the Black Hood!
Dad?
Mom?
Betty!
Dad?
Are you hurt, son?
Dad, are you okay?
Excuse me.
Thank you.
I guess Sheriff Keller's not looking
so bad right about now, huh?
There's a trapdoor leading
from the balcony to the roof
That's not on any building plans.
But I've got cars all over downtown.
He's not gonna get far,
we'll catch him tonight.
Sheriff, if I may?
Archie's come face-to-face
with the Black Hood before,
Looked him in the eyes.
Maybe he could help identify him.
You up for a ride-along?
Actually, I'm gonna head home,
stay with my dad.
Make sure he's safe there.
Yeah...
All right, then.
I just got off the phone with Betty.
Apparently, the Black Hood
just turned the town hall
Into his own shooting gallery,
while Fangs was right here.
So why is the Sheriff
still holding him?
What happened tonight
and what happened to Midge
Are being treated as separate incidents.
But if the Sheriff doesn't press charges
in the next hour, he has to let you go.
There are lots of protesters
outside, Jughead.
His release is going to make a lot
of people in this town very unhappy.
Mom,
You're shaking.
I'm fine.
Look, I know you want to be
strong for the campaign,
But if tonight was
any indication of what's to come,
Maybe you should drop out
of the race.
Nobody's withdrawing, mija.
Daddy, are you serious?
We've worked too hard on these plans.
We can't get skittish now.
A serial killer just played
target practice with mom!
Your father's right, Veronica.
This campaign is bigger
than what happened tonight.
I'll be fine.
He's willing to put your life
in jeopardy and for what?
His plan, his vision, his decisions.
You will show me respect in this house.
Like the respect you showed me?
When you asked me to entertain
the sons of your enemies?
Or the respect when I tried to tell you that
I'd worked everything out with the casino?
And you brushed me aside! Well,
guess what, I'm going ahead with it.
I've done the work
and I have the money.
Oh, you mean the money that you
swindled from the St. Claire?
Do you think I'd let my daughter keep
a pile of cash like that lying around?
I put it in a trust that you won't
be able to touch until you're 21,
When hopefully, you'll be more
rational and clear-minded.
Honey, I'm going to meet
your mom down at the register.
Actually, dad, I need to
talk to you about something.
I don't know...
What I saw at the town hall, if
that was really the Black Hood...
Cheryl and I went to your
sharebnb and broke-in.
You and Cheryl?
And I found this book
That the Black Hood used for
his cipher all those months ago.
Why do you have it?
I had no idea that
the Black Hood used that book.
All I knew was
it was your favorite.
You checked it out of the library
practically every weekend.
I found a copy online and I was
saving it for your birthday.
What? What are
you talking about?
You didn't think that...
oh, Betty...
Wait, wait. So...
This book is really just a present?
For me?
Of course, Betty.
What else would it be?
Dad, I just got back from
the Sheriff's station.
Fangs is getting out tonight.
Joaquin?
What's he doing here?
I called him.
He's going to help Fangs disappear.
I can sneak him out to San Junipero.
I got a place there.
Maybe. But first, we need to get him out
of that Sheriff's station in one piece.
There's an angry mob outside with pitchforks
and they're yelling for his head!
Something's happening,
and it's gonna make you
And the rest of
the Dark Circle very angry
And frustrated.
Fangs Fogarty
Is being released.
What?
Sometime after midnight.
But there's nothing
you or I can do about it.
Short of taking justice
into your own hands.
We must have faith in
the justice system,
Even if it sometimes allows the guilty
To walk free.
Ronnie, what's up?
I came here to see your dad.
Is everything okay?
Everything's fine, Mr. Andrews.
I just...
I wanted to tell you that from now on,
I'm supporting your run for mayor.
I can't in good conscience
Stand with my father anymore.
I believe in you.
Betty, is everything okay?
Dad?
I think we need to finish the
conversation we started earlier.
Should I come home, Betty?
No.
Meet me at the place
where this all began.
With my speech at town hall.
You understand?
Of course.
I want it to just be
between you and me.
Just how you wanted
it from the beginning.
Just like...
It's supposed to be.
Archie, you gotta get down here.
I'm down at the station...
Jug, slow down, I can't hear you.
I said, get your ass down
to the Sheriff's station.
Your guys are here
and they're out of control.
Oh, you mean the Dark Circle?
They're not my guys anymore.
Well, they want to rip Fangs apart.
He's getting out and we need
your help, Archie, please!
Justice for Midge!
Free Fangs! Free Fangs!
Free Fangs!
Okay, dad.
Let's talk.
You can't take Fangs out the front.
We have to take the side entrance.
Crowd's out there, too.
So pick your poison, Serpent.
What do we do, man?
I don't wanna die.
Fangs, you're not going to.
Look at me, okay?
We stand together
so none of us falls.
In unity, there is strength.
In unity, there is strength!
No!
I swear, mother, if this is one
of your gentlemen callers...
Synced & corrected by MaxPayne
== https://subscene.com ==