Previously on Riverdale...
- My dad, he's...
- A mobster.
Archie, it's not just what he is,
it's what he's planning
to do. In Riverdale.
I don't need to know.
Smithers, would you describe
my father as a good man?
I'd rather not say, miss.
Oh, my God! What happened to the twins?
- I had them, Betty.
- You didn't call us. Mom will be crushed.
He has to go, Alice.
Chic, he's kinda creepy.
I just remembered
where I knew Chic from.
He's a video gigolo, a web cam boy.
My parents, they know about
the affair with Sheriff Keller.
- I have decided...
- Mayor McCoy's resigning.
Hiram Lodge. He just bought
Sunnyside Trailer Park
and he said we can all stay.
He's gobbling up the
Southside piece by piece.
I was running out of time.
And maybe, so was Riverdale.
Hiram Lodge had been making moves.
Big moves. But with no
proof of criminal behavior,
all I could do was speculate.
What was Hiram's master
plan for Riverdale?
And why did it feel
so close to fruition?
Hey.
What's all this?
Hopefully, this is the article that
saves the town from Hiram Lodge.
- Jughead...
- If I can fit the pieces together.
Boy, you need to drop
this. He rescued us.
He bought the trailer
park, forgave our debts.
What? He's the reason we
almost lost the trailer park.
Hiram's slicker than a bottle of
snake oil, no doubt, but this is...
Dad, please!
Hiram Lodge just bought
The Riverdale Register.
He's trying to silence dissenting
voices before he makes his big play.
He's afraid. He's
afraid of this exposure.
If you remember
correctly, the only house
in Riverdale with a
pool was Thornhill...
There we were, two drunk, dumb
teenagers looking to cool off...
Why didn't you just go to the
quarry? Or Sweetwater River?
Oh, what I remember is
someone borrowing the school van
for a joy ride, you and Mary...
No, that was Alice, not us.
Oh, my God, this sounds like
an episode of Saved by the Bell.
Hey, Fred, before you
head off, why don't
you join Hermione and me in the study?
I have this 30-year-old
rum. I think you'll love it.
Well, I can't say no to that.
- Veronica, stay with Archie?
- Mmm-hmm.
Betty, I can't keep doing this anymore.
He's your brother and it is weird.
Kevin, every time I try asking
Chic questions about himself,
he gets defensive or literally
starts to cry as a diversion.
- You're catfishing him?
- If it's the only way to get Chic to open up.
I...
So, do you ever P and P?
You know, Party and Play?
You keep asking me that
and I keep telling you no.
You know...
This is our third time cam-ing
and you haven't really told
me anything about yourself.
Yeah, well, you haven't taken
your shirt off yet. So we're even.
I'm shy.
Okay. What do you wanna know?
What are they talking about
in there, do you reckon?
So, between us, the deputy mayor
who took over for Josie's mom
is on the verge of stepping down.
There's gonna be a special election
and my parents think your dad
would make an ideal candidate.
They want my dad to run for mayor?
It's business and politics, Archie.
They go hand in hand.
Dad, is this something
you're seriously considering?
Being mayor is something I dreamed about
ever since I was a little kid,
son, in the back of my mind.
And I know Riverdale's
had a lot of downs lately
but maybe, I can help get
it back up on an upswing.
And you don't think it's weird
that Mr. Lodge is asking you to run?
He's not dumb, son. He spends
a lot of money in Riverdale.
It makes sense he wants a
friend in the mayor's office.
Will he pay for your campaign?
He offered to make a donation
to help me get going, but...
But to be clear, Archie,
if I decide to run,
it won't be for him,
it'll be for Riverdale.
For me.
For you.
Mother. Strange man I've never met.
Cheryl, this is Mr.
Lazenby, our estate attorney.
Your father, as it turns
out, left a secret will.
Of course he did.
But Daddy died months ago.
And Mr. Blossom's instructions were
to reveal the existence of his will
only after the authorities had concluded
their investigation
into his side business.
You mean drug dealing?
Does this mean we're
gonna be rich again?
Oh, Cheryl, don't be so gauche.
Per Clifford's instructions, he
requested I withhold all information,
including the names of his numerous
beneficiaries, until
a public will-reading.
That's tomorrow afternoon.
It's been a long time coming, Alice,
but I'm out. I'm done fighting.
I want a divorce.
- Are you still seeing Penelope Blossom?
- No.
And this isn't about that.
This is about how I worshiped
you like a goddess for 20 years.
We raised a family together,
and then the first chance that you get,
you side with a stranger over me?
And you too, Betty. I can't believe
that you would choose Chic's
side over your own father.
Dad, if this is truly about
Chic, then I'm with you, okay?
Let's ask him to move out.
You sold The Register to
that scumbag Hiram Lodge.
I should be the one divorcing you!
Hiram offered me a fairer price, Alice.
Half of which I will give to you,
if you agree to set me free...
Immediately.
I'm listening.
I put the odds of Fred
saying yes at about 50-50.
As always, mija, anything you
can whisper in Archie's ear?
Mom, he's my boyfriend,
not a constituent.
Ah, you influence Archie and Archie
influences Fred, and
we need Fred right now.
When we announce our bigger plans...
It'd sound better coming out of his
well-respected, well-liked mouth.
Fine. I'll do my best.
Are you still going after Hiram Lodge?
Well, that depends.
Who's asking? You?
Veronica? The archfiend himself?
Jug, there's gonna be a special
election to replace Josie's mom.
- Hiram Lodge wants my dad to run.
- What? Why?
Who freaking knows? Jughead, I'm with
Veronica, so that means
I'm with the Lodges.
But my dad,
I can't let him get in
any deeper with them.
So tell him he shouldn't run.
Veronica would kill me if
I did. And ditto the Lodges.
Maybe I could give you something.
Maybe you could write about it and
that might make my dad hit pause.
Okay.
You remember when Hiram
Lodge gave Pop Tate
that charitable donation
to keep that diner open?
Yeah, we were all there.
Except Hiram Lodge didn't
give Pop's a donation.
- He bought the diner.
- What?
And for some reason, he doesn't
want anyone to know about it.
Can you do something with that fact?
At least enough to make my dad think
twice about this stupid mayor idea.
- He bought the diner?
- Yes!
God! Hiram is like Dracula.
Snapping up properties from all over
Riverdale to expand his empire and feed.
If what you're telling me is true,
everyone is in danger.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
I figured out Hiram's methodology.
He acquires devalued land at a deep,
some might say criminal discount.
Twilight Drive-In,
Sunnyside Trailer Park,
Southside High, and now
Pop's Chock'lit Shoppe.
- Wait, Pop's?
- Hiram bought Pop's?
Yeah. And while most people didn't
care about Hiram's other acquisitions,
probably because they
were on the Southside...
Pop's is the heart of Riverdale.
Right. People will care about this one.
So, when are you talking to Pop?
I was doing some
research and apparently,
your dad needs 1,200 signatures
- before he can even run for mayor.
- Uh-huh.
So I was thinking, if
you're not doing anything,
maybe we can collect them together.
You know what?
I actually have some homework
I have to catch up on.
- I'll talk to you later.
- Wait, Archie...
Polly, what are you doing home again?
She just walked through the
door with these perfect babies.
I thought it would be
nice to surprise Mom.
And I was surprised to meet our brother.
You have to hold one.
I'd love to.
Here.
Oh, hello.
Hey, where's Dad, by the way?
Are we all gonna go to
the will-reading together?
- What will-reading?
- What?
You... You mean Dad hasn't told you?
Cheryl, I agreed to come to this
will-reading but I didn't
agree to a makeover.
Unless it involves that blouse.
Nice, right?
For the record, j'adore
your flannel mesh aesthetic.
I'm merely augmenting
it for the occasion.
What is going on in here, Cheryl?
Mrs. Blossom, hi, I'm Toni Topaz.
I'm a friend of Cheryl's from school
and she's lending me an
outfit for the will-reading.
And why on Earth would you be there?
I invited her to be
my emotional support.
Just make sure you're downstairs
before the guests start to arrive.
We need to present a united
front against those scavengers.
Ugh. She's a nightmare.
Isn't she though?
Hey, Arch, check this out!
When I applied to college
to be an urban planner...
This is before Grandpa already got sick,
this was a presentation that I made
for some program I never got into.
Riverdale 2020. Small
town with a big future.
- Sounds corny, huh?
- No, Dad, this is awesome.
Hello?
Archie! Mr. Andrews?
Oh, goody! You're both here.
So I fully realize I'm putting
the cart before the horse,
but I was spitballing some design ideas,
and I think I may have come up
with a few potential campaign logos.
Veronica, those are terrific,
I gotta say, but... Oh!
- Now, that one, that's my favorite. Hmm.
- Mine too.
Great. So I'll have some buttons
and T-shirts printed ASAP.
Why are you pushing this on him?
I'm not. I just think your
dad would make a great mayor.
Why are you resisting this so much?
Because, Ronnie, my dad is not
cut out for what your parents want.
Which is what, in your mind?
A dog on a leash who
does what it's told.
And if not, they'll push him
out like they did Mayor McCoy.
Archie, Mayor McCoy had an
affair with Sheriff Keller.
That's why she stepped down.
My parents had nothing to do with it,
which I would swear to you on the Bible.
I feel like you're
steering me, Ronnie, like
you're steering my
dad, and it's not cool.
So ease off him.
Okay.
"I, Clifford Cochrane Blossom,
being of sound mind and body,
do here inscribe the terms
of my last will and testament.
Firstly...
Ownership of Thistlehouse
will stay with our beloved
matriarch, Roseanne Blossom.
To my wife and partner, Penelope,
I leave ownership of
our greatest treasure,
Thornhill, the exquisite
mansion she made a home."
The charred husk of an empty house.
That sounds about right, Mother.
Now, the reason I contacted you
and you all traveled to be here.
"Any and all remaining assets of
my fortune will be divided in half.
The first half will be distributed
equally to anyone in Riverdale
who can prove with
medical authentication
that even one drop of Blossom
blood flows through their veins."
I knew it!
- Alice, what the hell are you doing here?
- Accusing you publicly.
You only wanted a divorce
so that you could cheat me
out of your big, fancy Blossom payday.
It's not just my payday, the
girls share Blossom blood too.
My lawyer is gonna rip you apart.
Isn't that right, Attorney McCoy?
I will be taking half of
whatever blood money you get
from this inbred cesspool of a family.
Yeah, that's right. I said inbred.
Would you please just leave?
Shut your face, you
half-melted ten cent trollop!
Oh, this is riveting, I can't breathe.
- Usual, Jughead?
- Not today, Pop.
I actually have a question for you.
Did Hiram Lodge buy this diner from you?
Jughead...
The Tates have owned this
diner for over 80 years.
When my ma gave me the keys,
she made me promise that no matter what,
I'd always keep this shop in our family.
Now, I did what I
needed to with Mr. Lodge
but my mother's still
with us, God bless.
It would kill her to hear
I went against her wishes.
Please, Jug, can you keep this to
yourself while I still have my mom?
And then you can tell whoever you want.
Now that the interloper has
been escorted from the premises,
we can finish our
business. As I was saying...
"The other half of my fortune
will go to my true heirs,
Jason and Cheryl."
As the one true Blossom heir,
I feel it is my sacred
duty to say a few words.
The Blossoms have been bathing in blood
since Great-Grandpappy
Blossom killed his brother.
The original sin of Riverdale.
Well, I stand before
you to say, no more.
No more blood.
No more madness.
No more horror.
Here, here.
Oh!
Couldn't have said it better myself.
Ugh!
Oh, Mumsy, I had the
most frightful daymare.
Daddy was back.
Calm down, it's not what you think.
Hello, Cheryl.
I'm your Uncle Claudius.
- Twin to your father.
- Twin? But...
Daddy never said anything
about having a brother.
Well, allow me to explain.
When Clifford and I were boys,
we were inseparable,
modern-day Romulus and Remus.
And it became apparent that I was being
primed to inherit the Blossom empire.
Till our 14th birthday.
Clifford and I were down by
Sweetwater River and he, uh...
He pointed a rifle at me
and with eyes void of humanity,
he told me about the Blossom curse.
How one of the twins
always meets a violent
end and often at the hands of the other.
Well, he spared me.
But that very night, I ran
away from home without a trace.
It broke my heart.
I couldn't bear to speak your name.
I joined the Merchant Marines.
I sailed the seas desperate
to outrun the Blossom curse.
How soon do you think we could
get those blood tests done?
Do you think Dr. Patel
works on weekends?
- I'll call and check.
- Polly, what's the rush?
I just wanna know how much
money we're inheriting.
Between you, me, Chic and the babies,
we could start our own
version of the farm.
Uh, I'm not getting my blood tested.
Really, Chic, how come?
- Uh, I don't know these people.
- They're your cousins.
We're all Blossoms, like it or not.
I'm not, thank the Lord.
I don't want their blood money.
- Don't be stupid.
- I said, I don't want their money.
Besides, needles trigger me.
Polly, Betty, leave your brother alone.
He can decide for himself.
Mom, I decided something.
I'm happy to do the
family's bidding at school,
but Archie is off the table.
- You're losing your nerve?
- No!
Not even close, but I am
afraid of losing Archie.
He's become a pawn on our chessboard
and it's hurting our relationship.
Veronica, in this business of ours,
the women always walk the razor's edge.
The men are the gangsters, but us,
the molls, we use our wiles,
our cunning, a hand on an elbow,
a whisper in an ear,
to manage things from behind the scenes.
Maybe, but not me. Not with Archie.
You're right.
You're right to protect your
relationship with Archie.
We gotta get aggressive, Kev.
Chic's turning down a lot of money
because he's refusing
to take a blood test.
And we need to find out why.
What exactly is hishiding?
What am I supposed to do? Just ask him?
I have a plan.
It's slightly insane.
Hey, stranger.
Been missing your cute face.
Where'd you go?
Uh, yeah, sorry. I
went MIA. I actually...
Just got tested for
the first time and...
I'm negative but it's
been pretty intense.
Your first test? Congrats, cowboy.
- That's a milestone.
- Hmm.
Uh, do you get tested?
Yeah, I used to go every week.
Man, I had the worse scare once!
Oh, yeah? What happened?
Yeah, it's a long story but, uh...
I was living with a
rougher crew than I am now.
Wait, are you talking to somebody else?
Uh...
That's it, that's it. I'm out!
No! What do you mean, Kev?
Sorry, Betty, but your brother
actually seems like a really good guy
and this is starting to make
me feel like a really bad person
so sorry, but I'm done.
Well?
Did Pops confirm Mr.
Lodge bought the diner?
Yeah, he did.
But I'm sorry, I can't
publish that article, Archie.
It would break Pop's heart.
Jug, we can't give up. I
think my dad's gonna run.
Archie, I have talked
to every possible suspect
connected to the
Lodges, even Mayor McCoy.
They're all on lockdown.
Maybe you've been talking
to the wrong McCoy.
I'm brunching, Archie. What do you want?
My dad is seconds away from running
for mayor with the Lodges' support.
And I don't him to go
through what your mom did.
So I was thinking maybe you
could get your mom to talk to him.
Even secretly.
Archie, my mom barely made it
out of the mayor's office alive.
If she lets slip even a whisper
of what went down between
her and the Lodges,
there'd be hell to pay.
She'd implicate herself
in about a million ways.
Yeah, I figured.
But isn't there plenty of stuff
your mom could say to my dad
that would kill his buzz without
getting into the shady stuff?
It's not all ribbon ceremonies
and catered affairs, Fred.
It's filling potholes, collecting trash,
and if you think you can run this town
plus Andrews Construction
at the same time, forget it.
I've got a pretty good
team working for me.
And then there are the
uglier aspects of the job.
Crime, poverty, threats...
Like the Black Hood?
Right now, you might be the
people's shining hope of Riverdale,
but say you do win, Fred.
They'll turn their back on you,
and all your friends
will be standing in line
to stab you in the back.
I appreciate the real talk, Sierra.
I haven't even gotten to
the real talk yet, Fred.
Let's chat about the pittance
that is the mayor's salary.
I know.
Oh. Hello.
Mom! I'm late for
work, can you drive me?
Not right now, Chic, I'm with
the twins. Take the bus or walk.
Oh, hi.
Pop Tate, to what do I owe this honor?
Sorry to bother you at home, Mr. Lodge.
Come on in.
Apparently, Jughead Jones
is asking questions about the
ownership of the Chock'lit Shoppe.
- Jughead Jones!
- Daddy!
Did Pop Tate keep his mouth shut?
- More or less.
- Then Jughead has nothing.
No, what he has is someone from our
inner circle feeding him information.
Now, the only people that know that
we own Pop's are the three of us.
And Archie Andrews.
And yes, he's proven his
loyalty to us, but what's to say
he isn't feeding information
to his best pal, Jug.
It was me.
I told Jughead about Pop's.
- What?
- Why?
When we were all at Shadow Lake,
Jughead was grilling
me about the Southside,
asking incessant questions about SoDale,
the trailer park, Southside High.
I had to get him off the scent,
so I distracted him with the
smallest truth I could, the diner.
Veronica, so help me, that is a...
- That was quick thinking, mija.
- What?
You can't possibly think
that was a prudent choice.
I do.
Veronica wisely threw the dog a
little, relatively harmless bone
to keep him from digging up a much
bigger, more controversial one.
Yes, exactly.
Her gambit bought us the time we need
for some preemptive damage control.
Ojala, you two are right.
Hiram's gonna beat the clock.
Feels like every step I make,
he's two or ten steps ahead of me.
He's lapping me!
He's been winning at this game a
lot longer than you've been alive.
Yeah, because he's been rigging the game
and everyone's too afraid to
come out and speak against him.
You know, uh...
There's one person you haven't asked
to go on the record yet.
Who?
Me.
You know, back in the day,
Hiram asked me and the Serpents
to trash the drive-in so he could
buy it for rock-bottom price.
We complied.
On purpose?
You worked for Hiram Lodge?
I'll own up to that.
On the record, if it'll
help you bring him down.
- Hello?
- Jughead Jones?
I have information about
Hiram Lodge's plans.
Riverdale bus terminal. 20 minutes.
Who was that?
I have no idea.
But you may not have to
go on the record just yet.
I'm gonna kill you.
You're leaking private
information about my family.
Information that my
father trusted you with.
- Look, if this is about Pop's...
- Damn right it is!
And lucky for you, I fell on the sword
and saved you from
his apocalyptic wrath.
- You didn't have to that.
- Yes, I did.
If my dad ever found out you snitched,
do you know what he would do to you?
Veronica, I'm not gonna apologize
to you for trying to protect my dad!
From my parents?
Archie, this isn't The
Manchurian Candidate.
And your father is an untouchable.
He'll never be hurt or corrupted.
What happened to your loyalty?
We brought you into this because
you said you were fine with it.
- You made a promise!
- Veronica, you wanted
my eyes wide open before
I committed to your family.
You insisted upon it, in fact.
And if my dad is gonna run
for mayor with your parents,
he deserves to know the
whole truth and so do I.
What whole truth?
His big secret plan for the Southside.
You were almost gonna tell me at
your confirmation but I stopped you.
Well, now, I wanna know.
For myself and for my dad.
That's... That's something you'll
have to talk to my dad about.
Oh, hey, there you are.
- Hey, Veronica.
- Hi, Mr. Andrews.
Perfect timing. Uh, I have
an announcement to make.
You two are looking at the next
candidate for mayor of Riverdale.
Guess you better talk to my dad fast.
Wasn't better when it
was just me, you and Mom?
Uh... You... You don't like Polly?
Love is finite.
People run out of it eventually.
They stop loving you or they
start loving someone else.
One day, the sun is shining down on you,
and the next, you're alone.
And it's cold.
And dark.
Chic...
Are you okay?
Don't use my bathroom again, Betty.
I haven't much time.
Are you Deep Throat?
You've been calling everyone in town for
information about
Hiram Lodge but not me.
That's why I called you.
No offense, but how does a bus driver
have insider information on Hiram Lodge?
I used to be someone else,
someone who was privy to
Hiram Lodge's personal affairs.
Someone who suffered at his whims.
What kind of personal affairs?
I coordinated
transportation for Mr. Lodge,
sometimes out to Shankshaw Prison.
He also received mail
from the warden there.
Shankshaw?
That's not where Hiram
Lodge served time.
I'm afraid that's all I have for you.
That's it?
And one more thing. A question.
Miss Veronica, how's she
faring through all this?
So, Mr. Blossom, how does it feel being
back in Riverdale after all these years?
Ignore that person, Claudius.
I'd assumed tonight
would be family only.
It's all right. I enjoy
meeting new people.
Do you know, during my
journeys as a sailor,
I came upon the most wonderful island...
- Lesbos.
- Oh, my God.
It is the most beautiful
natural place on Earth.
Oh, you're not going back on
the boat, dear boy, are you?
You're staying here with us.
Whatever I can do to make
sure that you and this house
are well cared for, Mother.
That is, of course,
as long as I'm welcome.
There's a room over the garage.
It's freezing in winter
and boiling in summer but...
It's there.
So, Hiram Lodge's
master plan has something
to do with your old
stomping ground, Shankshaw.
I tried calling the warden a dozen
times but he hasn't called me back.
That corrupt son of a bitch.
Do you have any contacts on the
inside that might know something?
Yeah, War Baby.
He knows everybody's business.
Can I get in to see him?
Can I just say, between
us, that Chic is creepy?
I don't think he likes me and I
don't think that he likes the twins.
A couple of times I've just
caught him, like, staring at us.
Yeah, tell me about it.
It's part of the reason
why I submitted a sample
of Chic's blood to the lab
that the Blossoms set up.
- CSI Nancy Drew!
- Yeah.
How did you get a sample of his blood?
Don't worry about it.
But Polly, I think that Dad may be right
that Chic's dangerous,
possibly not even our brother.
Well, what do we do if he's not?
Well, it'll crush Mom but
we'll have to tell her.
In a way, it may kind of be a relief.
Hey, you're home.
Yeah, Polly just spent her Blossom
inheritance on silk headbands.
Betty, keep your voice down.
However Mom got Juniper
and Dagwood to sleep,
I do not want them waking up.
- Oh, no, the twins, they're not home.
- What do you mean?
- Where are they?
- They're with Chic.
He wanted to take his niece and nephew
for a walk along Sweetwater River.
Why? Is there something wrong?
Mom, are you serious?
How could you let a complete
stranger take my babies?
He's not a stranger. He's your brother
and he's doing something nice for you.
Yeah, the hell he is!
What did you do to my babies?
Nothing, Polly. They're fine.
What's up, Jonesy? You want me to
knock some heads in here for ya?
No, War Baby, we need intel.
You heard about anything major
going on behind the scenes?
Maybe to do with a guy named Hiram?
Hiram Lodge?
You're like Dracula.
He bought property all over London
so he could move his vampire
kingdom over from Transylvania.
Except you're bringing
organized crime to Riverdale.
And you want my dad to be mayor
so he can be your patsy, except...
What if you and him don't
see eye to eye on something?
What an imagination you have.
- What do you have there?
- This is my journal.
When Mrs. Lodge sent that
fake FBI agent to test me,
I started taking detailed
notes of everything
I saw while I was apprenticing with you.
- Is that a threat?
- I'm looking out for my family.
Archie...
I believe your father and
I will make a great team.
Moreover, in 18 months,
Lodge Industries will
be 100 percent legitimate
and Riverdale will be
virtually crime-free.
The safest small town in America.
How are you gonna do that?
Or am I not inner circle enough to know?
Everything will become clear very soon.
I'm just asking for you to trust me.
Forget about me. This is my dad
we're talking about, Mr. Lodge.
We will all benefit from
this, Archie. I promise.
I'll hold you to that.
And in the meantime,
I'll keep this very close.
- Where's Betty?
- With Jughead.
- Why do you ask, Polly?
- I...
I... I'm going, Mom.
Chic said it would only be a matter of
time before you left
us for the farm again.
I'm not going to the farm, Mom.
I'm driving west, San Francisco, maybe.
It's a nice city,
Polly. I've been there.
It's safe too. Safe for the kids.
Will you at least let me say
goodbye to my grand-twins?
Of course.
Drop us a note with your new
address when you get there.
Okay?
Hey.
What's wrong?
We just got a call from our good friend
Warden Jeffries at Shankshaw Prison.
Seems that Jughead and FP Jones
paid a visit to one of FP's cronies.
A well-informed, loose-lipped crony.
We think they know, Daddy.
Think they know everything.
Which means it's just a matter of time
before Jughead splashes it on
the front page of a newspaper.
One we do not own.
Get Fred and Archie over here now.
Hiram Lodge is diabolically insane.
Agreed. We need to show
Riverdale just how insane he is.
This is the best thing
you've ever written, Jug.
Principal Weatherbee needs to
publish this right the hell now.
Let's go.
Jughead Jones may be
about to break a story.
A story about my plans for Riverdale.
And rather than hear it from him,
I think it's only right
that you hear it from me.
This is quite a story, Mr. Jones.
Thank you, Principal Weatherbee.
Unfortunately, it's not one
that the Blue and Gold can print.
Why the heck not?
A malicious take-down of
one of our students' parents
is not the appropriate subject
matter for a school paper.
Now, if you'll both excuse me.
You're serious? Southside
High is gonna be turned into...
A private, for-profit prison.
Yeah, built on the
bones of a high school.
What the hell have we
been building in SoDale?
What we've said all along. Housing.
For all the people who
will work at the prison.
And you expect me to
support this as mayor?
We're hoping you'd be open to it.
Yes.
- Can't do it. I'm outta here.
- Look, Fred...
We've been in business for how
long? And you didn't tell me.
And the only reason
you're telling me now
is because it's getting
ready to become public.
I'll admit, it's not ideal.
"Not ideal," Hiram?
You wanna turn the town
that I love, my home,
my son's home, into a prison.
Fred, please let me tell you why and how
this is the right move,
for us, for Riverdale.
You just save that for whoever it
is that you find to run for mayor
because we are leaving
and we are leaving now.
Come on, Archie.
Dad, I'm gonna stay.
Excuse me?
I wanna stay. I wanna hear
what Mr. Lodge has to say.
Then I will see you at home then.
Thank you all for coming.
Ladies and gentlemen, I give you
your next mayor of Riverdale,
my mother, Hermoine Lodge.
Thank you, Veronica, and
thank you all very much.
Like many of you, I grew up in this town
dreaming of a better tomorrow.
For myself, for my
family and for my friends.
And now,
for the future that you all so deserve.
Riverdale is one of the most
dynamic, resilient communities...
The Lodges. How often have I dreamt
of getting my revenge on them.
Now, now, Claudius. First things first.
Nana... Then Cheryl.
Of course, Penelope.
Our house must be put in order.
Riverdale cannot succeed
unless all of us succeed
and that will require
certain sacrifices.
What... What is this?
When you wouldn't
submit to the DNA test,
I found some of your dental
floss and sent it to the lab.
Those are the results.
You're not who you say you are, Chic.
So, who are you?
We will also need your support.
We will need your trust.
We will need your loyalty.
I knew a prison would
be a difficult sell.
Especially with Fred.
I was gonna ease him into the idea.
And clearly, I should
have told you both sooner.
I regret that.
To be honest, Mr. Lodge,
before Jason, before the Black Hood,
before my dad was shot,
I might not have understood
your point of view.
But I've changed and I think
Riverdale needs a change too.
This tradition has
been in my family,
going back generations.
It's a...
sign of loyalty.
Once you do this,
there's no undoing it.
No changing your mind.
So are you certain?
I think...
I am.
You know what you need to do.
Now, Archie...
We come first.
This town has endured so
much these past few years.
After so much adversity,
aren't we all ready for
a taste of prosperity?
And there it was. The Lodges had won.
Time had run out for Riverdale.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --