Help! Help! Help!
It's-it's Rev. He's hurt bad.
What?
I went in, and he was...
Take me to him. Now.
Wait, he was...
He was right here.
I-I saw him.
I-I held him.
- Don't touch anything.
- I already did.
Touch him.
I came in and he was lying
right here on the ground.
Your brother is missing, too.
Do you think Manny might
be in danger as well?
I-I don't know. I hope not.
I suggest we work quickly
with what we have.
Now, it seems
the perpetrator was startled.
- Otherwise, why leave the knife?
- Oh, Andre, stop.
Everything should be
preserved as evidence.
No one should touch
the murder weapon, right?
I got my powers back somehow.
Do you think it's because Rev...
Your powers came back?
Can you handle things here
while I look for my brother?
I got a bad feeling about this.
Okay, just keep
in close contact.
Don't worry, we will get
to the bottom of this.
Cover up all the BS.
What the hell are they thinking?
This is private property.
Hey! Hey, y'all, stop that!
I should've known.
- Y'all with the 44orum now?
- We're with the right people.
Y'all need to leave
before I show you
exactly what I'm capable of.
You think you can stop
all six of us?
Try me.
Little something
for your poster freak.
Let's get out of here.
All we know is
there was blood and no body.
Let's stay calm and
figure out what to do.
She did it.
Is that why you came back,
to finish the job?
I was here the whole time.
But you can move things
with your mind.
You wouldn't even need
to be in the same room.
What? Hayden, you know that
I can't do that.
I don't know what
you can do anymore.
I should have trusted my vision.
What are you saying?
- You think you saw me - kill Rev?
- No.
Just-just you leading people
in here to hurt us.
We all saw what you did
to Bill Greene.
That was to save my sister.
It was all for Millicent.
- I'm not a killer.
- Everyone,
we are innocent until proven
guilty. And with no body,
we can't even know for
certain what happened.
So let's stop pointing fingers.
Let's get answers.
I had really hoped that
coming back here was
the right thing.
I'm sorry, little chicken.
I didn't want to kill you.
I just wish I could
bring him back to life.
Like that wouldn't be creepy.
Why do we have to
keep eating meat?
Have you met Karenna,
who got here last week?
She was telling me about
something called veganism.
Millicent, Caleb taught us all
about the importance
of the food chain,
and our place in it.
It's our way of maintaining Zen.
Yeah, I just don't know why
we can't bring our Zen
to everyone.
Mom dumped us here
when you were eight, Millie.
Don't you wonder what the rest
of the world is like now?
This is my world.
And out there is exactly
what Caleb says it is,
filled with selfish
irresponsible people,
just like Mom.
Not to mention drug addicts
and predators and, hello,
Charles Manson.
Not veganism.
We have everything we want here:
Safety, education, a future.
And out there it's a fight
every day.
They'd probably just
see us as freaks.
Okay, I guess I see your point.
When Caleb gave you
your community bracelet,
you said it with him.
The we is more important
than the me.
And I can't wait to get mine
when I turn 18.
Oh, come on, I'm right.
I knew coming back here
was a bad idea.
First thing that goes wrong,
and of course it's my fault.
Okay, look, that was bad
down there.
But it's gonna be okay,
all right?
Shanice has search parties
spanning out around the building
looking for Rev.
And we all know
you didn't do it.
No, we all don't.
I'm going back to Claudette's,
'cause she trusts me.
No. Mildred, stop!
Look, I know you didn't do it.
A 44orumer must have
snuck in here and got Rev.
They are our real enemies.
I heard they're setting up camp
on a street nearby.
It's like Occupy Wall Street,
but for white supremacists.
Look, these are bad people,
Mildred.
I'm just gonna have to
take my chances out there,
because if Hayden thinks...
He's just scared.
He told everyone
that I'm a cold-blooded killer.
How am I supposed to prove
to everyone that's not
- who I actually am?
- Fine.
You should talk to
Claudette, but tomorrow.
It's not gonna help your case
if people see you sneaking
out of here tonight.
Besides, maybe in the morning,
we'll know
what the hell happened.
Right?
The cops on their way?
I haven't called them yet.
They'll just treat us
like suspects when we don't
even know what the crime is.
How are you holding up?
I keep seeing his body.
Lying there, and...
And I came back,
and he was just gone, Shanice.
I-Is this somebody's superpower
or something? I mean,
what the hell is happening?
We're all scared. I have teams
scouring the hotel
for any sign of Rev
o-or clues to what happened.
- Should I help?
- No, Logan.
You have been through enough.
Hey.
Logan, you holding up?
Ready to be in my own bed.
As the only witness, I'm afraid
I need to ask you to stay.
At least until you talk
to the authorities.
Let's hang on a minute.
He... A crime was
committed, Shanice.
We still live - under the
laws of our country. If,
God forbid, the culprit is
a 4,400, imagine what happens.
The public
turns further against us.
It might even supersede
our sanctuary
and make us all fair game.
And besides,
we need to find Rev first.
- No body, no crime.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
There was a body. You have
to believe me. I saw him.
Okay, we do, Logan.
Okay.
We keep it internal.
For one day.
I'm still sending
Logan's clothes and the knife
- to a friend in the lab.
- Thank you, Keisha.
Let's just hope
the killer doesn't strike again.
I wouldn't be surprised
if the 44orum were behind
what happened to Rev last night.
I can't believe they came
to bust the place up.
It breaks my heart to say it,
but your Steve
was among the perpetrators.
He's not exactly my Steve,
but still.
First my dad, and now him.
Do you...
Do you see what I mean?
They're turning everyone
against us.
You really are safer at
the Bois Blanc, dear.
Where everyone thinks I'm going
to use my powers to kill them?
Now that I have them back,
I just want - to use them for good.
Well,
I'm grateful they've returned.
We're gonna need them
for whatever the 44orum
is planning.
Oh, which reminds me,
those children left something.
They said it was for you,
but I don't quite
know what it means.
This is Millicent's.
- I thought she was at Ypsi Med.
- So did I.
This is even worse.
The 44orum have her.
Let's go get some iguanas.
What the hell?
Isn't it illegal to take up
- an entire city block?
- I guess
the cops are giving them a pass.
Which is more than we'll get
if we get caught.
There's still
an active tip line, remember?
Oh, my God.
I shared a van with that psycho.
You know, they think
we're iguanas, Mildred.
They want to dissect or kill
or stuff us or whatever.
- That's why we have to find - Millicent and get out of here.
- Okay, look,
I'm not gonna let you fly solo,
but I still vote
for Claudette
gathering reinforcements
like she said she could
when she saw
how determined you were
- to do this.
- I can't wait.
If we find trouble,
our powers will
get us out of it.
Trust me. But I have
to save Millicent.
For real this time.
As we say
before each bounty,
we give thanks to these animals
for their lives
so that ours may be productive.
Everything in symbiosis.
Everything Zen.
We give thanks to the earth
for giving us life.
I'm starving. Everything
in symbiosis. Everything Zen.
I'm excited to eat, too.
- Give thanks to each other.
- No.
Caleb's not done with his...
Well, someone...
has put their needs
above all others.
Millicent, would you care
to explain
why you were "outside world"?
She's just hungry, Caleb.
It won't happen again.
Oh, would that explanation work
for a hit?
Hmm? An insult?
Your sister is a senior youth.
An example.
When this happens once,
it's alive in your mind
to happen again.
Her actions
water the seeds of selfishness.
- I'm sorry, Caleb.
- Don't be sorry.
Be Zen.
Take your pulse down.
Take it down.
That way, your wants
will never take precedence
to the community's needs.
Millicent.
I'm gonna hold onto this for you
until everyone else finishes.
Eat.
I'm sorry, Millie.
I should have stopped you.
Ah. They said I'd find you here.
How's Logan doing?
He's asleep, thank God.
I was actually
looking for Hayden.
We searched every inch of this
place for any sign of Rev.
Came up empty.
I thought maybe the
vision he mentioned
could lead to a clue, but
I can't seem to find him.
Well, that's concerning.
Especially as nothing's
adding up. I spent
the night with Keisha
at the "crime scene,"
as she kept calling it,
trying to parse out the details
of what may have occurred.
If Isaiah's
body was moved,
there should be a blood trail.
Instead, there is none.
And if the killer is a 4,400
who can make things disappear,
then why leave the knife?
None of it makes sense.
And unfortunately,
Logan is our only witness.
Uh, then maybe it's time
to rouse him.
I was thinking,
if there could be
two witnesses... No, Andre.
This is exactly
why I got rid of my powers.
Y-You want me to ask him
to revisit his trauma
so I can experience it, too?
No. No, I can't.
Well, just like my abilities,
we have to accept
the consequence
for their benefits.
If there's anything
to be gleaned
from a review of Logan's memory,
it may catch a killer
and let us sleep
better at night.
Miss Claudette.
Was hoping you'd be here.
I, uh, heard about the vandals.
Look, do you think
that has anything to do
with what happened to Rev?
I wouldn't put it past them.
With our former gatekeepers
filling out their ranks,
they now have experts
on the geography
of the Bois Blanc.
Ken seems ready
to do real harm to us.
You have any leads on Manny,
either? Jharrel's been
asking about him.
Sounded in a state.
I do not envy the challenge
of trying to find
an invisible man.
I-I'm sorry, come again?
Did you not know
about Manny's ability?
No. My partner
conveniently forgot
- to tell me - that little detail.
- Do you think that...
That Manny
didn't just go missing?
I don't know.
I'll see if his brother does.
Whatever they're getting
ready for, it is not good.
That's why we have to find
Millicent and get back.
Wonder what her power is.
When I saw her briefly at
Ypsi Med, I couldn't tell,
but they had her in a - hood
and a straitjacket. Millie?
Millie!
I can't believe it's really you.
- You look so much older.
- I was taken
two years after you. You look
just the same as I remember.
I missed you so much.
Millie, you look so beautiful.
- So do you.
- Hey, earth to Millies? We got to go.
Right. We've got to go. Now.
Millie,
find your Zen.
You, too, LaDonna.
Seriously, Millicent,
we need to leave.
- Now.
- But why?
We have everything we want here.
Out there,
it's a fight every day.
I'd like for you to see that.
I need for you to.
Millie!
Millie! Wait, what's going on?!
- Take them inside.
- Let me go!
What are you doing?!
We got a couple iguanas here.
Millie, please! Millie!
So, you just h-hold my hands
and read my mind?
Sort of.
I can see the memories
of what you're thinking about.
- But it's all a blur.
- It's... That's okay, Logan.
This isn't a test.
I-I just want to go home.
I-I already lied to Mariah
and told her that Hayden
wanted me to stay the night.
She's at Mrs. Grover's.
We all want to go back
to our lives.
Whatever that means these days.
Okay.
So, I-I just...
Rev?
Rev, can you hear me?
I'm going to go get help.
Did that help?
It was just as you said.
I thought I was saving
my sister, not a traitor.
I'm sorry for the dramatics.
My bracelet to get you here.
The hood.
The fact that LaDonna's
in the next room with a gun
to her head if you try anything.
You were at Ypsi Med.
I saw them take you
down the hall.
After I was stolen from Caleb
by the green light
two years after you abandoned
his guidance,
I was taken there
almost immediately,
where Bill Greene,
who you tried to kill,
offered nothing
but reason and kindness.
No, Millie,
you don't understand.
He's a liar.
Just like Caleb.
I knew you would say that.
Which is why I brought you here.
It's you and your 4,400
who need guidance.
You tried to kill a man.
To save you.
Does that logic hold?
Kill to save?
Is that what your reverend
taught you?
This isn't you, Millie.
What are you talking about?
You are a 4,400.
You're working with the people
who want to get rid of us.
These people
think you're here
to get rid of them, actually.
Which your internationally
televised tantrum confirmed.
Millie, your 4,400
are a selfish,
irresponsible people.
Like Mom.
Your Bois Blanc sanctuary
is a cult.
You need to be saved.
- You can't be serious.
- Millie...
Look at me.
We know each other.
We've been there for each other.
Even when it seemed
like we weren't.
Remember?
Yes.
Remember that you are the future.
It's your responsibility
to keep each other safe.
The outside world
intends to inflict harm.
It's how they turn you
into one of them.
And how do we aim to stay?
What's the state of being
that puts the we
over the me?
Millicent.
Zen.
That's right.
We stay Zen,
they can't harm us
at any distance.
You're not centered.
Your pulse
is on fire.
Now you've destabilized
your sister, too.
- Sorry.
- Do you see how quickly
bad energy can spread?
That, my children, is how the me
destroys the we.
Now,
let's get washed up for chores.
And I need to see you later.
We have to leave.
What?
- We have to leave here.
- I know
sometimes Caleb is scary,
but it's for our own good.
- It's for our Zen.
- We should
be able to keep that
in the real world.
Why do we need him
to monitor us?
I'm only a few years away from
getting my community bracelet.
Caleb said
that I could start classes soon.
I can teach you
the good parts of it myself.
I have the bracelet, remember?
- Come on.
- How?
How could we possibly... There's a bus.
It stops at the south side
of the commune.
It could take us to Oakland.
Please. Mildred.
Please. If Caleb
is telling the truth,
then shouldn't we take our Zen
to those who really need it?
Okay.
If you
promise that you're going
to take care of me,
then I'll go with you.
Of course.
Shanice? You look shaken.
Are you okay?
I, uh...
I thought I'd taken a step
closer to normal.
That I'd hit a rhythm here.
Have a chance to understand
this life that I now have,
and-and then my powers
came back.
And then I had to see...
Isaiah
like that.
And... And then...
I think Rev was taken
by a green light.
Like... Like the one
that brought us together?
This is remarkable.
I am terrified, Andre.
What does it mean
if they're back?
Maybe it happens in death?
Maybe we were always
meant to go back.
So, this can disappear
in a second? Like the lives
- we have already lost?
- Let's not get ahead of ourselves, Shanice.
The implications are worrisome,
but we don't know anything
for certain now.
So, what do we do?
I think we keep this between us
for the moment.
Our conjecture
could spark further panic
in people already on edge.
What if our perpetrator knew
about the green light?
Or came from one?
And considering
that your powers returned
before Rev's body disappeared,
maybe this ZMT
that Manny said is in our blood
is somehow related.
His levels dropped.
So did his power's efficacy.
Let's submit a request to BHN
for items to aid
in our research.
A centrifuge,
a semi-auto analyzer
- and as many pipettes - as they'll part with.
- Andre,
what's going to happen?
A question people
have asked for eternity.
Only we...
have the most unique
of circumstance.
And we have each other.
For now.
That we do.
I thought I told y'all
not to come round here.
Jharrel?
What on earth are you doing?
I don't know.
I'm still just trying
to find Manny.
Using his code back at him,
hoping he'll
return to Room 437,
where I found him with it.
Seems like he doesn't want to be
found again, now, does it?
I know how this looks for him.
I was worried when I heard
everybody's powers came back.
Now Keisha just texted me.
Said she has something
for me to see, and I...
I don't know. I'm
beginning to feel
like I don't know my brother
at all.
I have to tell you something.
I saw your brother.
Here in 2021
weeks before you did.
He said his name was Jorge,
and he offered to train me.
Wait, what?
When you thought I went away
to bartending school,
I was here with him
and other 4,400s
learning what we need to know
to be ready.
- To fight back.
- Okay. Wait, wait.
I-I don't get it.
Why didn't he tell me this?
- Why didn't you?
- Jharrel,
one of the things
I like most about you
is your heart is on your sleeve.
- I knew you'd never accept - our course of action.
- You trying to justify
- what Manny might have done - to Rev?
- No.
No, there's nothing just
about it.
But sometimes bad things
have to happen
for the greater good.
There's no progress
without pain.
Says the lady
who's learned to deny it.
Maybe Manny will have
a better explanation.I...
Jharrel.
There you are.
I've been looking all over
for you.
I was worried
you'd also disappeared.
What are you doing down here?
I don't think
Mildred's done killing.
First Bill Greene.
Then she shows up here
like nothing happened,
and then Rev dies?
I-I think she killed him
to get her power back
and then hid his body
as part of her bigger plan.
- Is this - about the vision you had?
- Yes.
I saw her bringing people
through there. Armed people.
Look, I never wanted
to believe it, but now I do.
- Look, she is - gonna attack us.
- Hayden,
it is hard having visions.
Trust me, I know.
We're stuck interpreting
things we don't understand.
But if we start jumping
to conclusions,
if we start basing what we think
on the narratives
the media is creating,
we become our own enemies.
So, what should I do?
I'm glad you told me
about the vision,
and I'll share it with the
others so we're on the lookout.
But honestly,
I think it would
make Logan really happy
to see a friendly face
right now.
Okay.
Thank you, Shanice.
I can untie you
if you want to eat.
Is it laced with something?
See?
Suspicion drives you.
It's not healthy,
Mildred. I only want
what's best for you.
For all the 4,400.
Which is what? To kill us all?
It's actually
to protect you all.
Join me, and I can tell you how.
But none of us
want to kill your 4,400.
Really? Is that why
there's a gun to LaDonna's head?
That would be you killing her.
- These people have you believing - things not based in reality.
- So,
they're supposed to accept
that we time traveled,
but it's their version
of things that's deluded?
Do you hear yourself?
Your 44orum want us dead,
Millicent.
Nobody has ever said that.
Meanwhile, are you trying
to tell me "Embrace Your Power"
isn't meant to incite violence?
Does that sound Zen to you?
I'm sorry
for what happened back then.
I still can't believe
we're actually
going through with this.
I'm so lucky you're my sister.
In life.
Not just in here.
I hope you keep thinking that.
Why wouldn't I?
You told him?
I had to save us, Millie.
No.
We needed to be saved from him.
Millicent.
I'm not angry with you.
Much of what we investigate
is making your own mistakes
as long as you're willing
to learn from those mistakes.
Everyone seeks to
run away from that
which asks a lot of them.
That's why selfishness is god
to so many.
I just wanted to see
what the real world is like.
That's like saying
you want to know
what it's like to feel sick.
Millie, I love you.
Please, come home with us.
I'm sorry, Caleb.
I'll never be so selfish again.
Well done, Millicent.
Well done.
Thank you.
For realizing
that this is the right choice.
I realized after we went back
that...
I trapped us.
You saved me that day.
I finally found my way
with Caleb's guidance.
And then a year later
I was heartbroken
because I thought
you had been tempted and left.
I thought about leaving once
after I realized
how it actually was with Caleb.
What he did to you.
But that's not what happened.
I know what happened.
This happened.
Do you think it's a coincidence
I was brought back to you?
Tell me, does your 4,400
embrace you, Millie?
Would you say
that your life with them is Zen?
Because I can see in your eyes
that it's not.
They haven't been great to me.
Whereas I
have never felt safer.
Despite my designation.
I think you're right.
I can't believe I
didn't see it before.
I'm so sorry, Millicent.
Just...
Just please tell me
how I can help.
- You're lying.
- You can't brainwash me.
No one ever will again.
Wake up, Millicent.
Appreciate y'all coming
on such short notice.
And a special...
What's the saying?
Shout-out to Nelson
for bringing us what we need
to save my headstrong friends
who I knew
wouldn't heed my warnings.
Is Jorge coming?
We are in charge of ourselves
for the moment.
But remember,
he picked each of us
because we can handle our own.
It's one of those guards you told us
to be on the lookout for. Steve.
He alone?
Seems to be.
Claudette, I... Get in here.
What's your business?
I, um... I came to apologize.
And to warn you.
I swear, in the alley
the other night, I don't know
what I was thinking,
okay? Doing what people did
to my parents' shop.
And your warning?
Ken reported you
to the tip line.
Accused you
of "power threatening"
and assault of
a government-contracted officer.
He's just waiting
on the paperwork
to get back to us
and be approved,
and with accusations
this severe,
they'll take you
to a black site.
At least now they
just come on out and say it.
It's not black like that.
It's... But isn't it, though?
Whether it's the 44orum
that's believing we are iguanas
or the government
detaining us as terrorists,
this story ends as poorly
as it always does for us.
For all of us!
Unless we write it.
Now go on back to your brethren.
We could use a man
on the inside.
- I'm sorry.
- Stop being sorry, Steve!
And start getting mad
at the right people. Go.
Now we have even more reason
to get the hell on out of here.
- Hey.
Ah, to think.
One day ago, we were
the happiest we've been here.
And BHN
certainly pulled out
all the stops.
And now they're concerned
about 44orum buildup
outside the hotel.
Said they're gonna send a rep
to assess our security.
How do I even tell
them what's happened
in the building?
Not that I'm even sure.
Which is why I need to continue
my research.
When you spoke
to our benefactors,
did they mention my request?
If they declined my appeal,
I can take it.
No, Andre.
They actually want
to meet in person.
Outside the Bois Blanc.
Which is why I didn't
want to tell you.
I can't have you go
out there, Andre.
- They're not wrong - about the 44orum.
- I will be careful.
A field medic knows
how to navigate
hostile territory.
But who's to say BHN
isn't also the enemy?
Or maybe
we're so cynical already
that we're passing up
a golden opportunity
to help ourselves.
- We have to trust - someone eventually.
- I don't agree.
I only trust who I know.
I don't want you to put yourself
in harm's way, Andre.
You know
I can take care of myself.
And I want to go.
For you.
For everyone.
Open up, Claudette!
This is your last chance!
You're in here somewhere.
Not a lot of places to hide.
Hey.
I hope you're presentable.
Did you hear that?
Yeah. I'm-I'm scared, Mildred.
I'm so sorry, LaDonna.
I thought that I knew
what I was doing.
I thought that I knew my sister.
Like I thought I knew my dad.
You're safe now.
Proud of yourselves?
Did you guys take out
an entire street?
Place was practically
a ghost town.
We only had to subdue
a few of them.
One of them tried to poke me
with this.
Those boys and their
Confederate toys
that make them
feel like patriots
when really they
act like traitors.
That's a light cavalry saber
used at Antietam.
You one
of those Civil War buffs?
No, I... I was there.
All right, y'all can do
your little meet-adorable
or whatever later.
We have to get out of here.
The 44orum is on the offensive
planning something big.
Mildred, let's get your sister
and hightail it.
No, wait, it's not that simple.
- She's one of them.
- I beg your pardon?
Millicent lured me here
and tried to convert me.
They have one of us
on their side?
- Do we know what her power is?
- She didn't tell me.
Then we have even less time
to waste. We have
to get back to the bar
to get ready.
Take it you haven't heard
- from your brother?
- Despite leaving the ciphers, no.
Look, I'm worried about him,
Keisha.
You should be.
But for everyone else's sake.
He thought he left
a pristine crime scene,
but he forgot one thing.
And once the Feds find out
they're looking
for an invisible man,
you can be damn sure DARPA's
got the technology to catch him.
Just wait. Please, Keisha.
- Manny must have a good reason for why he's doing this.
- His reasons
are purely selfish, Jharrel.
As are yours
for trying to protect him.
Just thought you should know
what's coming.
I'm gonna need
whatever's in that bag.
What the hell, Jha?
- Oh, so, this is you - testing me now?
- No, bro.
This is us catching a killer.
We were counting
on you eavesdropping
on our investigation. Keisha
said that you would show up
if you thought
you were gonna get caught.
I was really hoping
you wouldn't.
Now talk.
Or we will literally drag you
to the police station.
- Let me tell you why.
- Why what?
Why I killed that reverend.
Oh, my God. You did do it.
With what's coming, the 4,400
cannot have somebody
taking away their powers.
Turning special people
into the ones
that are trying to oppress them.
- So you stabbed him?
- I heard
he tried and failed to give
Mildred Bell her powers back,
so something more drastic
was called for.
You may not believe me,
but I'll carry this with me
the rest of my days.
It was still
the right thing to do.
- And what did you do - with the body?
- What? Nothing.
Once I disappeared again,
I got the hell out of there.
So that's why you killed him?
Just to get your powers back?
With what's coming,
I needed to make sure
all the 4,400
were fully charged.
Okay. So,
- what's the plan?
- You lead the team into the hotel.
Be at the ready.
LaDonna,
can you illusion us both
so we can get close
to Millicent?
Probably easier
than a mess of iguanas.
We appreciate
you towing the mark.
This would all be so different
if I'd just listened
to her back then.
But as soon
as I finally understood,
she was a true believer.
And I got zapped
before I could save her.
This is my chance
to do the right thing.
This is not your fault, Mildred.
We can't change the past,
but our future
isn't written yet.
The 4,400 in that hotel
need you with them
whether they know it or not.
They are your family now,
and you have to protect them
while we do the same.
All right?
Y'all be safe.
None of you know the Bois Blanc
like I do,
so stay close behind me.
Let's go.
So, you really expect us
to believe
that you did this
for the good of the 4,400?
I just want the 4,400
and both of you
to be prepared
for the inevitable.
Oh, yeah? And what's that?
Your trial
for first-degree murder?
Check the 44orum.
Tell me what you see.
It's time to save
you God-fearing patriots
from these threats...
This is outside the hotel.
To our way of life.
Your families will never be safe
if we allow these freaks to make
our inner cities
even more dangerous.
I have to warn everyone.
And let them know
that we caught you.
Hey. Please,
tell me you are not one
of the 44orum.
I'm not, bro. I swear.
Okay, then what the hell, Manny?
How do you know what you know?
You're not ready to hear it.
You know, Claudette
said the same thing to me.
Because apparently,
you are her mentor.
- Well, she's a quick study.
- This isn't a game, Manny!
She is out there thinking
that she is indestructible
because of her powers and you.
I care about Claudette.
Not about what she can do
for me. About her.
So if you know anything
about what's happening,
you better tell me now.
Come with me to the window.
Here we go. 44 no more!
Get in, Dr. Davis.
There won't be another chance
to get the answers you seek.
It's getting loud out there.
I know.
That's why I'm glad
Keisha has a suspect.
I can go home
and get us to safety.
Look, honestly, Mr.
Kaminski, I can stay.
That's out of the question,
Hayden.
Mariah's at Mrs. Grover's.
That's where I'm taking us
until all this can blow over.
- Come on.
- Then you seriously need to get a move on.
The mob is growing
by the second.
Are you sure it's even safe
for you both to leave?
We've got to try, Shanice.
- Is anyone watching the tunnel?
- Right now,
let me get you to safety.
Do it! Do it! Do it!
So, this is all you somehow?
You know as well as I do that
this is just America in 2021.
What I've done is to make sure
we all get the right outcome.
- For once.
- What the hell
does that mean, Manny?
I didn't come here
from a year ago.
Stop lying to me,
Manny. All right?
I saw the green light.
True, Jha.
But it didn't take me to 2021.
It took me to 2062.
And I'm here from the future
to make things right.
Captioning sponsored by CBS.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org