Rise and shine, Doc.
Oh, good. You're up.
Glad to see I'm not the only one
spinning their wheels
this early.
So, what have you discovered
about our superpowers,
Dr. Watson?
I see. You're Holmes, then?
Obviously.
Have you made any headway
deciphering that gibberish
we found in Manny's book?
No. Somehow, I'll need to find
a coding book to understand
what each line means.
I also wish I could check
my FOMOSnap
to see if my video
made it out to the world.
I may have leaked
a little something to show
what it's really like in here.
You know, hopefully get us out.
But we have to keep this
on the DL.
The down-low.
Just keep this
between us, okay? Understood.
Okay, great. Now,
I've been tracking time lines,
since the abilities seem
to emerge somewhat randomly.
I'd also like to understand
if the abilities
have any effect on the body.
Okay.Now...
what do you say to
a little experiment?
Sure. Why not?
I'd simply like to assess
your baseline vitals
while at rest and then again
when you are using your ability.
Okay. I'll have to use my 1920s
methods to record all this
until I can get access
to proper equipment.
Now try one of your illusions,
and I shall take
your pulse again.
What was all of that?
Oh, just some stuff
from Grey's Anatomy.
I never saw any of that
in my copy.
You must have read
a more modern edition.
All of that spectacular display
and your heart rate
slowed somehow.
Fascinating.
I am determined
that, together,
we can solve what is surely
the greatest of all mysteries:
These abilities
some of us possess.
For now,
we'll keep them on the DL?
Yeah.
Okay, everyone, simmer down.
I'm sure you've heard
about the leaked video.
Hell, at this point, it seems
the whole world has seen it.
Okay, so they're gonna
do something about
the conditions in here, right?
The conditions were
exaggerated by that video,
which helped no one.
The FBI is currently
investigating the leak
and will act accordingly.
That video showed the truth.
What the public is upset about
is that these people are
being treated like prisoners.
The plan has always been
to release them.
In fact, given the video,
we are moving up the timetable.
We're letting them out?
We are rolling
out a pilot program,
Project Reintegration,
to get some of our folks
out into the world.
We will be allowing
a select few out for a day trip
here in Detroit. This is
just another PR stunt.
The mayor's office
will be helping us coordinate
some minor press
around the event, yes,
but this is a stepping stone.
No, it is parading them
around for cameras
like animals in a zoo.
Would you rather
we never let them out?
The world is aware of them.
So make sure
that it goes smoothly,
and they'll all be
getting out soon enough.
Yeah, but what about the fact
these people claim
to have traveled through time?
The public, and, honestly,
even some of the people
who work here,
have other theories, too.
Like aliens or sleeper-cell
terrorists or...
Are we disproving
any of these theories?
Right.
All we can do
is show the public that
we've been careful to ensure
that they're not
a threat to society.
Other than that,
we can neither
confirm nor deny anything.
That is the official party line
until further notice.
And I expect you all
to hold that line.
Hey.
So I hear
we might be getting out
earlier than expected.
Some kind of video or something?
Heads up.
Thank you all for gathering.
We have some good
news to share today.
Tomorrow we launch
what we are calling
Project Reintegration,
a stepping stone
in your release.
Now, it's only gonna be
a few of you from this
facility for now.
But a number of other facilities
will be participating as well.
And it's gonna start
with one day out.
One day?
It-it's a start.
It's a step in the
right direction.
The hope is, eventually,
everyone will get out.
I would like to be
one of the first,
so that I might visit
a modern medical facility.
It would help me
to better utilize my skills,
and to be of real service.
I hear you, Dr. Davis.
But unfortunately, for now,
we can only let out
a few at a time,
and those four have
already been selected
at random by the government.
Random, my ass.
They are not gonna pick me.
And they've already
called me a troublemaker
for playing a piano.
Okay.
Those folks will be getting
the first day passes will be
Isaiah Johnston...
Shanice Murray,
LaDonna Landry
and Claudette Williams.
If this goes well, they say that
you'll all be getting released.
And we are gonna do our best
to ensure that that happens.
Look, I heard you in there.
So, I figured
you could work from here.
Well? What do you think?
Huh. Looks like it's seen some
festivities back in the day.
But why are we here?
Well, it's the old hotel bar.
This is just so you can
have a little space to...
I don't know, spread out.
Not have to work from home.
Trust me, we all
got sick of that.
This is a space, yes,
but what about equipment?
What about access to a lab,
or modern advances in medicine?
Look, I know you want to be
out there in the world today.
Okay? I want that for you, too.
But keep your head down,
and hopefully you'll get
picked for the next day out.
Please, don't insult
my intelligence.
Shanice and Claudette
most certainly
did not keep their heads down.
You must know
that their selection
doesn't make any sense.
Yeah, I do.
I'll put in a word
for you to be on the list
next time.
Please do put in a word
to allow me my freedom.
Just two weeks ago
I was conducting research
that was going
to change the world.
Old Dr. Weavers
would be diddling away
in obscurity
if I was not there
each night to check
and double-check our results.
We cured seven of our ten rats
all because of my diligence.
Poor little things, you made
them sick just to cure them.
And cure
I did.
It is all for science, my dear.
Knowing that my research
will cure bronchial infections,
well, that is something
for the books.
And it will only enhance
my residency status
at our very own hospital
in our own neighborhood.
Here's to our own Dr. Davis,
proving that the Negro doctor
has indeed arrived.
Hear, hear.
Just be careful
at that Harlem Hospital.
I hear the nurses dorm
has all sorts of lovelies
to get you in trouble.
Oh, no, no. My man does not
have time for all of that.
Do you, Doctor?
Come on in here. Dance with me.
Okay?
Are you quite done with all
the work discussion?
Better?
This is the first
night you haven't slept
in that dank lab in a while.
You keep promising me we'll see
Gladys play at Hansberry's
and do some real dancing.
Mm. When?
Soon, my love, soon.
My work is important, Cynthia.
Just you wait,
it'll all be worth it,
those nights in the lab.
I promise.
Hey, I have to run, Doc.
I hope this space helps
until it's your turn.
Soraya texted you, too? Yeah.
Said she found something
on the Belle Isle footage.
Whoa, what... Step aside.
I didn't do anything. I don't
know what any of this is about.
Yo, what is going on here?
Why is she in handcuffs?
I didn't do anything.
Hey. What's going
on with Soraya?
Why'd she just get
hauled out of here
like public enemy number one?
Yeah, forensics ran sweeps
on our computers,
and hers was the only one with
access to the leaked footage.
You think she leaked that video?
Why? I don't know.
Honestly, it's just
one less thing
hanging over my head right now.
Can you do me a favor
and make sure
nothing goes wrong tomorrow?
And Keisha's already met
with Claudette and Shanice
about where they'd like to go.
So would you like us
to contact family for you both?
We can probably get them
out here in time.
I do hope to reach out
eventually.
But I want to learn
what I can about what's happened
in these intervening years
before I do.
I owe my son that much.
Okay.
How about you, LaDonna?
Your mom's been reaching out.
Um, no, that's okay.
Seems like a whole hassle.
But maybe next time.
I a... I actually was
thinking a library.
The library?
Really? Wh... Yeah.
I mean, I need to,
you know, brush up
on fashion and gossip
that I missed.
I'd enjoy that.
And I'd like to go
to a house of God.
I hear Detroit has
some beautiful old churches.
Okay.
Let's do this.
Where's Dr. Andre?
I don't know,
but you want to see
something cool?
I kind of did it to Shanice's
ankle monitor by accident
when we were hanging out,
and no one came to get her.
Now she can just take it off
and on whenever she wants,
and the guards can't tell.
Ah, wonderful.
You're both here.
I hope to have your
help in figuring out
why some of us have powers,
why some of us don't
and how they all work.
Sounds groovy.
Let us take
a baseline pulse first.
I was born this way.
It wasn't an accident.
All right.
So, what kind
of a doctor were you?
I was a medic in the Great War.
When I returned, I ran a clinic,
but then I began focusing on
respiratory and bronchial issues
in my research.
It was most groundbreaking.
It was indeed
a splendid affair,
and I raised
the remaining funds needed
to move us to human trials.
And would you believe,
they loved the story
of how that last rat
was the final subject I cured.
I even told them
that it was my assistant
that named him Gustavo.
With all due respect, sir,
I would appreciate you
not referring to me
as your assistant.
Andre, focus on what matters.
We are so very close
to curing whooping cough,
and eventually
all bronchial diseases
with this new chemical medicine.
We both know it's the work
that truly matters. And we both know
I am the one in the lab
all hours.
I am the one
taking the calculations
and refining the treatment.
I should receive
the credit I deserve.
Andre, you should be pleased
I mentioned you
in the first place.
Till tomorrow.
Earth to Andre.
Ah. Yes.
My apologies, Shanice.
I'm just, uh...
Focused on your work.
Yeah.
Any insights
into these... powers?
Not as much as I'd like.
If I could just get access
to what I need,
I know I could find answers,
but my hands are tied.
I know it's frustrating,
but you don't have
to solve it all right away.
That's easy for you to say.
You're allowed out in the world,
instead of being trapped in
here like a rat in a cage.
And a useless one at that. Look, I know.
It's not fair.
I tried to stand up
for you, too,
when we met up with Keisha... I know.
It is appreciated.
Are you certain about
not seeing your daughter
on your first official outing?
I am not certain of anything.
I feel like I barely made things
right between us, and...
I don't want
to mess it up again.
And I don't know who I am
to Mariah or Logan.
It's been 16 years for them.
He's remarried.
But I was just married to him
two weeks ago.
Am I just supposed
to flip a switch?
Uh, please,
enjoy your time with,
uh, your Mrs. Grover.
Thanks.
Yeah, I think Claudette
will enjoy meeting her, too.
All right. Well,
do come and see me
when you get back,
so that I can add your
data to my records.
Will do, Doc.
Feel a little more
normal already.
I'm really not sure this skirt
is at all appropriate.
Well, they did offer you pants.
If we're going to see live music
after visiting your
Mrs. Grover like I asked,
I am not wearing pants to dance.
You can bet
your business on that.
There is a lot
of people out there.
What do they want?
A spectacle.
Maybe I should just
sneak out again.
You know what?
We don't have to feed
everyone to the wolves.
Excuse me?
Yeah? Can you escort these two
to the loading docks where
there's no press or cameras?
Roger. This way.
Thank you.
Uh, what are you doing?
Our details are out front.
Did you see them?
They don't want to do this.
Do you really think going rogue
is a good idea?
Look what they did to Soraya
because they think
she leaked the video.
Do you really think
taking a different exit
is gonna make them
throw the book at us?
Yes. My public is here.
You okay with this?
It'll be good
for them to see us,
to realize we belong out there.
Let's go.
Hi!
Oh, yeah! Who's good?
So, this is Detroit, huh?
I barely recognize it.
It's... it's different.
There's... more.
I love this city, but...
I'll have to get
to know it again.
All this,
the cars and-and the people,
and the buildings.
Oh, I never imagined.
It's better than
what you imagined?
Different.
Y'all aren't faking this.
No, we never lied
about what happened to us.
You really are from 1958,
aren't you?
Neecey!
And friends.
Y'all come on in.
I made a batch of my famous
Grover's Mules.
Come on. You, too.
Come on.
LaDonna, lovely
to see you again.
And Reverend Johnston, hi,
I'm Carla Coleman
from the mayor's office,
comms director.
Let's get a quick photo
of you both
in front of this
signage over here.
And then I'm thinking
we just grab some candids
around the library
as you go about your business.
Sound good? Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
So, I was actually wondering
if they were gonna
use you for this.
Hmm. Okay, be honest.
Don't you feel a little,
uh, goofy babysitting
some grown adults in a library?
Oh, I feel
completely ridiculous.
But the only person
I'm here to babysit is you.
So you're still holding my press
conference meltdown against me?
Well, I saved your job,
didn't I?
You did.
Thank you, CC.
Well...
I know you care
about these people.
I'm just hoping this can help.
Maybe we should take,
like, a laughing one.
You know, the Carla I knew
was gonna be a journalist,
someone who would
seek out the truth
regardless of what the cost.
We were gonna fight the man
together, now you are the man.
What happened?
Real life happened, Jharrel.
You know this is how it works.
And I'm sorry,
some of us need a paycheck
and can't afford
to go running our mouths
whenever we feel like it.
Look, no, I didn't mean that...
Yeah, you did.
You always think
you're the only one who cares.
Let's just get this over with.
Young Hayden.
I was waiting for you.
It's your turn, remember?
I just don't like being
poked and prodded.
Or strapped down.
I can assure you, I won't
be doing any of that.
I'm trying to figure
this out for all of us,
so that we can understand
and control these powers.
Did Mildred tell you
we made great progress?
She's coming in for further
observation later today.
I-I just had a vision.
May I?
All right.
Tell me about it.
Yeah, um...
I was holding some flowers
that I think
were for Mildred.
That sounds lovely.
I mean, she was
my first... kiss.
It was nice, but...
I've never had a girlfriend.
Is this how it feels?
How about this?
You help me with my research,
and I shall teach you
what I know about women.
I will even teach you
how to dance.
Dance? Mm-hmm.
I don't know.
Oh, every woman
loves to dance. Baby, won't you please.
You were right, my love.
This is just the work break
I needed.
You know, I love our
little breaks,
but maybe next time, don't
bring all your work home
in the first place?
I brought my work home
because I'm tired of being
under Dr. Weavers' thumb
all the time.
I'm on the verge of
a breakthrough... Ah!
Silly me. I thought
you brought it home
to spend more time with me.
But I never get to see you.
You're always puttering
and moving about, never resting.
How's this...
for moving about?
All right, Doctor.
Well, how long have you
had this cough?
Is there any blood, too? My love...
it's nothing, I promise.
I just got a little excited.
Co-Come back to me.
Yo, Isaiah, you doing all right?
Is it possible to find
someone on this thing?
Where they are?
Yeah. Who you looking for?
I just want to see
what happened to my
family's church after I left.
I got you. All right, use this.
Search for yourself
or your family.
Right.
Okay, maybe try adding
"Reverend" in front,
and/or "Chicago"
to narrow down the search.
Hey, you two.
So, what'd you find? Oh, yeah.
Uh, you know, just my ticket
to the trends
in fashion that I missed.
Speaking of that, so I saw that
the '90s and '70s
are coming back,
like, all at once;
Seriously, what gives?
I really couldn't say.
How about we get those
checked out for you?
Of course you found a way
to profit from my death.
I held my breath
as Michelle and Barack
strolled down that boulevard.
Oh, she looked so beautiful.
And he's a handsome man.Mm-hmm.
So handsome.Mm.
Aretha Franklin performed,
and then Beyoncé for his second.
What, from Destiny's Child? Oh, no, child.
We way beyond that now.
We in the era
of Black Lady Excellence.
Or so the kids call it.
I can't believe I missed
witnessing all of this.
All the hard work that
brought us to this point.
Well, you're here
to witness it now.
And be a part of it.
Cheers, ladies.Cheers.
Uh, maybe they should
switch to water.
Maybe theycan make
their own decisions
about what theydrink.
I'm going to make
a call outside.
Now, now, you two.
She's just doing her job.
Did she tell you
what happened to you all?
We don't know what they think.
They're not telling us anything.
And there are a few things
that we aren't
telling them, either.
I-I am not sure
I fully understand it.
Well, spit it out, Neecey.
Well, ever since we came back,
many of us have powers.
Superpowers.
So, let me get this straight.
You're saying that
when you touch someone,
you see their memories?
Well, it only happened once
with Mariah, and...
I don't even really
know how I did it, or...
Okay, then,
what did you see?
I saw...
I saw her call Bridget "Mom."
Tell her that she loves her.
Neecey,
Bridget's been there
taking care of her
most of her life. I know.
I know that.
Give it some time.
This whole situation is
all kinds of strange.
But I was just... It seems to me
you've got to stop
focusing on the past.
Be in the present.
Figure that out first.
Then you can figure out
how you want to
move forward with them.
They might just surprise you.
She's got a point there,
Shanice.
Now, do you see memories, too?
No, I...
and thank God I wasn't
raised by that man.
I was given a legacy
before I was even born,
and it's a legacy
that I don't want.
This conversation, reparative
therapy, is the real sin.
There is nothing to repair.
We have always been here
and always will...
Hey, man.
It's time to go.
Okay. I'll meet you outside.
Hey, what's up?
How's it going over there?
So far, so good.
Just finishing up
with a few more pics.
Kind of the same here.
Nothing out of the ordinary.
I have to admit it does
seem pretty normal.
Like they should be
out in the world.
Catching up on it all, I guess.
Ah. Okay, see,
I like this Keisha.
But trust me, these people are
just like you and me.
In a situation
beyond their control.
I have to go.
Everything all right?
That was very good,
Miss Mildred. Now...
let's increase
the level of difficulty.
What do you think
they're doing out there?
Enjoying having the freedom
to do as they wish, I suppose.
I don't think I want to go.
I have Hayden and Shanice,
and a whole room to myself.
It's not so bad. I see.
Now.
Do try to lift these bottles up,
all at once. I want to see
if our results change
with several heavier objects.
Keep them floating
as I check your pulse.
Good!
Amazing.
Look.
I can't!
So you just gave him a place
to do experiments,
unguarded? I...
To, like, study and stuff.
Hell, I didn't think it was
that big of a deal.
Well, Jessica is pissed.
It was a freak accident.
We're on a path to
getting these people out,
and there's still so much
we don't know.
Oh, come on.
Did anything go wrong
on your outing today?
No.
Nothing went wrong, but...
But they're from the past.
What could that possibly mean?
I don't know.
It is something unexplainable.
We still don't know what's
going on with Soraya
or the thing on Belle Isle.
Or how this freak
accident happened.
Trust me, I know, but...
But let's just
take the win today.
All right? We took some of these
people out, and it went well.
So you think Keisha saw
my hand heal?
So stupid of me
showing off like that.
I don't think so,
or Miss By-The-Book
would have said something.
Hey, hey, hey.
Did y'all hear about Mildred?
They sent her to Ypsi Med.Yeah.
Dr. Davis did something wild.
Destroyed the old bar.
I heard it was dope.
I mean bad.
Shattered glass everywhere.
Is Mildred okay? And Andre?
We don't know.
We're waiting to hear back.
All right, get ready.
You guys are like astronauts
coming back from the moon.
What's going on?
You find out anything
about your son?
I have no son.
Oh, my...
She was fine
the last time I saw her,
and now she's gone.
What did you do to her?!
Hayden!
I'll make sure she's okay.
And how will you do that?
You don't care about us.
All you care about is
your experiments.
If you really cared,
Millie would still be here.
I told you
I didn't trust doctors,
and you proved me right.
He's really upset
about Mildred, isn't he?
You okay?
Well... well, here, Doc.
These should cheer you up.
I got some of the medical
books you asked for.
I got 1924 to 1930.
Disguised them as
fashion magazines
to hide them from
Big Brother, of course.
Another DL operation, I presume?
You know it.
And I also got myself
a coding book, and an actual
fashion magazine.
Oh, my God, these,
like, lockdown looks.
The amount of high-end
loungewear and slippers
is ridiculous.
And, like, designer
surgical masks? Mm-mm.
It looks like we lucked out
missing all that.
I did it.
What'd you do?
I... have the most
wonderful news.
What is all this?
I convinced Dr. Weavers...
to give you a spot
in our human trials.
I even asked him to assign you
our lucky number seven.
We've been over this, Andre.
I'm not one of your
little guinea pigs
for something that's untested.
But it is tested.
My treatment works.
Your data will add to the others
and help with the cure.
Now, Gustavo here is...
Andre, you did not bring
that vermin into my house!
I mean it, you need to
get all of this out of here now.
This is where we live, Andre.
Cynthia, my love...
Just listen.
I know you are scared.
And I am very worried
for what might happen
if you don't get this treatment.
My work will cure you.
I know it will.
You have to trust me.
Dr. Andre's not what
I need right now.
I need my loving partner,
my sweet man
to just be here for me.
Don't you understand
the importance of this work?
Work?!
Is that what I am to you,
just work?
This cure will save the world.
It's not just about you.
Don't be selfish.
Mm-hmm. I think that we need
a bit of space, Andre.
I'm going over to my sister's,
and you can have
this whole damn place
to do your work.
Cynthia, my love. Please, wait.
I brought you your usual.
Surprised you wanted
to meet up with sellout.
Look, I'm sorry about before.
I know I should just be happy
these people are getting out.
Not be so concerned
with the how.
And I know that you were
just doing your job.
But you were right.
I'm sorry, what...
Don't let it go to your head.
I'm just as frustrated
at this whole PR charade
as you are.
Look...
the mayor wants the city
to take custody of the 4,400.
Here, in Detroit. Be a part of
their reintegration
into society.
Okay, that seems great.
Yeah, but the Feds
have stonewalled us.
PR is all they'll let us handle.
They won't let us in
on any logistics,
or information gathered.
Yeah, but they're saying
they don't know anything.
Yeah, then why not let us in
on what they got?
Why not be transparent
with their local partners?
You think that
they know something.
But the question is what?
Did you know magnolias are
quite resilient?
Live in many types of climate.
They may seem as delicate
as a honeycomb,
but they are not.
They represent long life
to those who give
and receive them.
Maybe you could
give those to Mildred
when she comes back.
This is what I saw.
I-I was right, but not...
These are "get well" flowers.
And I think she'll love 'em.
But what is the purpose
of seeing the future
if I couldn't see
if she'd get hurt?
A-And if I can't see
if she's all right now?
What if something's wrong,
and I can't help?
I think these powers
aren't a solution to everything.
But I also think your
Mildred is very strong.
Just like those magnolias.
I was too consumed...
with proving that
I could help Mildred,
help everyone, that
I lost sight of her.
There was a woman in my past.
Cynthia.
She was sick,
and I was so certain
that I could help her.
She-she didn't make it?
Oh, she did.
I found out that I...
I did cure her.
But in our last moments
together,
all I cared about was the work.
I didn't listen
to what she needed.
I-I could have been there
for her, at least...
at least for the time
that I had with her, but...
I was too consumed.
I-I'd hug you, but, um,
I don't know what triggered
that vision with Mariah,
and I don't want to invade
or see something
that you don't want me to... Shanice.
I don't want to make
that mistake again.
I don't want to pull away from
the people that I care about,
and I...
I care for you.
I should tell you something.
I'm...
I'm not like the men you know.
Yeah, I know.
I like that about you.
No, I...
I must tell you that
I am not like...
like your Logan.
You mean because he's white?
Here.
This might be the best way.
I want you to know me.
It's okay to use your powers.
But I don't know how to...
Just try to focus.
I shall, as well.
When I was born,
they said I was a girl,
but clearly, I'm-I'm not.
I'm transgender.
Trans... gender?
So, are you...
Are you like Noah, then?
Yes, uh...
I think...
I am.
Hey. Hey.
So, how many chandeliers
did you break today?
Here.
This might help. You're amazing.
I can't believe the only
thing that went wrong today
was at the hotel.
Especially after headquarters
decided to let out
our two biggest troublemakers.
Oh, you mean Shanice
and Claudette.Mm-hmm.
Why did they do that?
Probably hoping that
something would go wrong
so the public could see
that the 4,400 are
the problem, not the government.
But everything went great
with Project Reintegration,
so there goes that narrative.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
I just...
No, it's fine.
Well, how about we don't
talk about work anymore?
And take advantage... Oh...
of this office of yours again.
Did you lock the door? Always.
Gustavo?
Did the green light
get you, too?
Captioning sponsored by CBS.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org