Wow, you weren't lying.
There's a whole
BestTime section.
I still say the Sours
are the only way to go.
Uh-uh, no. The original
BestTime Bars are aces.
Okay, well, then, uh,
we'll just get both
for the trip. How's that?
Mm. You're gonna love
Niagara Falls, Hayden.
The fresh air, the mist.
Oh, just maybe go easy
on the road trip games, Dad.
Ooh.Wow.
Oh, no, I-it's okay.
I love games.
And my mom always wanted
to take me there,
so thank you all.
Sure.
Oh, my God, Hayden,
I have to show you all
the ice cream flavors. Come on.
Uh, yeah.
We made the right call
taking him in.Yeah.
It's nonstop publicity for them.
Like Detroit doesn't have
other concerns.
Oh, come on, Bridge.
You know,
not everyone's like us.
I mean, some of the guys
on my crew
want nothing to do with them.
I am so glad we're
getting out of town.
Everything's set
for Mariah's school, right?
Logan.
You owe her nothing.
Shanice is her biological
mother, Bridge.
Who wants to be a part of her
daughter's life, might I add.
It doesn't mean she needs
to sign every form.
But she doesn't... Especially one
allowing Mariah to miss a week of school.
She doesn't need to, but...
But you want her to.
It's not "want," Bridge, it's...
Look, I don't know, but...
I can't pretend like
she's not a part of this.
The mayor is so appreciative
you're willing to host
the Meet the 4,400 event.
We really feel the 4,400
and their whole story
are a boon to Detroit, and
we want the world to know it.
Hey, we are an open book here.
Right, Jharrel?
Besides, with my office
right up there,
I am guaranteed
a front-row seat to a
Gladys Keller interview.
Live and in action.
How'd you land her, anyway?
Well, we had a number
of outlets reaching out,
but the mayor really wanted
to give it to a Detroit native.
4,400's response
has been good, too.
Turns out a lot of them
are really into telling
their side of the story.
Speaking of, I have a new
addition to the lineup.
But we need to vet them.
I'll have my assistant
send over my addition.
See you guys mañana.
You don't like him.
Okay, when have I ever
liked the powers that be?
It's more than that.
Okay, yes, you're right, but...
I don't know, the...
I just want this whole thing
to go well.
Well,
I've been thinking about a way
to really show the public
there's nothing to fear.
Show them
a true 4,400, non-4,400
blended family.
Make it clear they're
just like you and me.
Wait, Shanice?
And her husband's
family that took inNo...
a 4,400 as well.No.
They're the perfect, beautiful,
multiracial poster family
that's really gonna
sell this thing.
I don't know.
I mean, it's... complicated.
And asking Shanice
to go along with it
isn't exactly a picnic, either.
I can come with you to talk
to Shanice if you want.
For your big interview?
Watched some video
on this Gladys Keller,
she's got a silver tongue
that trips people up.
Does that make you
the pot or the kettle?
Something on your mind, Shanice?
Any particular reason
you're helping Bill Greene
trick our fellow 4,400
into signing these
predatory contracts?
It's a standard agreement. It's not.
It allows the government
to trigger conservatorships
over everyone who signs
if certain "conditions"
are met.
What happened to our sanctuary?
Instead, you are
backing his play
to take away
your followers' rights.
He's kept his word.
Conditions here are good.
People are happy.
Bill is lying to your face.
They know we have powers.
And whether you want
to believe me or not,
I am pretty sure
they're gonna find a way
to use them against us.
So, if you are planning
another public spectacle,
maybe keep that in mind.
You okay?
It's nothing.
I just couldn't sleep, so...
trying to tire myself out.
Come on, Logan.
We both know you're
seeing Shanice tomorrow.
You know, we're all
she's got, Bridge.
I understand that, but
you were still picking up
the pieces of her disappearance
when we met, and that was
nine years ago.
Don't let this take you back
to where you were, Logan.
I'll mull it over.
I promise.
And promise me you'll shower
before you come back to bed.
Okay, hot stuff?
All right.
Love you. Love you.
Oh, come on. Mariah, you're
always stacking the deck.
What do you got?
Ooh, watch yourself, hot stuff.
I can't believe we finally
get to leave for the first time
since the pandemic started,
and the Kaminskis are headed
to Niagara Falls.
I know.
I haven't been on a road trip
since I was a kid.
Oh, and camping's
gonna be great.
Oh, come on. The world
is just starting
to open up again, but we
still have to stay safe.
I know. Which means
getting a little creative, but
it's nothing we can't handle.
I'll get it.
Yeah? Yeah.
What's over there? Absolutely nothing.
What do you got?
You're really...
You're grown!
Mariah, who's at the door,
sweetheart?
Logan?
Oh, thank God.
Shanice?
I'll admit, I've enjoyed
your delayed
departure to Mrs. Grover,
as it's allowed for
our dalliances.
No one says "dalliances"
anymore, Andre.
Well, I do.
Are you sure you have to leave
in a few days?
Yes,
since I refuse to sign
that stupid contract.
I mean, we both do.
Right? Have they found
you an apartment?
Uh, well...
I didn't know how to tell you
this sooner, but...
I've signed the contract.
Andre, no.
These conservatorships
are essentially a prison
sentence if triggered,
and I have to believe
they are planning
to trigger them somehow.
Why? Why-why would you sign?
It was before you found out
how restricting they were.
I plan to find
my own lodgings, but,
with all these people coming in,
I want to be here
to take care of them.
I learned my lesson
with Mildred and Noah.
I don't want them
to have to rely
on government medical personnel.
Please don't be cross with me.
How can I be mad at you
when I'm just worried
for you, Andre?
Sorry.
Uh, you're early.
Yeah, I, uh...
just thought the sooner we get
this taken care of, the better.
This is Andre.
We've met. We've met.
Thank you again
for your assistance
in escorting Mildred back
after everything.
Always there for my daughter.
Hayden, now, too.
Right, yes, uh,
Logan just wants me to sign
some paperwork for Mariah.
She's only missing a week
of school, but, uh...
You know, I-I thought
you deserved to be included.
Thank you.
You might need this.
You want me and Logan
and Bridget
and Mariah and Hayden
to get up there and pretend
we're some big, happy family?
A united, Rockwellian family
is always good for optics.
Look, I know it's weird,
but it's just for one day.
And I promise you
I know what a difference
perception makes.
And we need for people
to see you all as human beings.
Yeah. We make it clear that
the 4,400 are everyday people,
with family and loved ones, just
like everyone else in Detroit.
Yes, everything is just
so incredibly normal.
Listen, it's a story.
Every image that ever changed
history required a narrative.
I've been a part of enough
news cycles to know.
And we're hoping you
could convince Logan.
I hope you'll consider it.
I got to get back to the office.
Thank you.Mm-hmm.
Jharrel, I'm worried
about this event.
I can't tell if Rev
is in our corner or not,
and I don't trust whatever
the government has planned.
Yeah, me neither.
All right? But I do trust
that Carla knows
what she's doing.
Look, one way to beat them
at their own game
is to get the public
on the 4,400's side.
And what about
the conservatorships?
Well, it'll be harder
for them to utilize
those unlawful tactics.
The world rallies
around the people
that they're trying to suppress.
So, one big, happy family
with Logan it is.
I'm sure they would
love to have someone
with your press savvy
to participate, LaDonna.
I, for one, am staying far away.
Yes, I have explored
the machine you left,
and I am searching
for the remainder
of the COBOL code.
I...
Actually, I'm on a mission
regarding that
at this very moment.
I'm so sorry, but I will
check in again soon.
Hello, my good sir. Uh, hey.
You know, how's it going, doc?
Well, I miss my partner
in mystery.
How is LaDonna doing
at her dad's?
She seems glad to be there,
and for that I am gratified,
but I would like to follow up
on something she was working on.
Do you happen to have any more
of your brother Manny's books?
You know what, I was actually
about to head
to Claudette's today.
Because I got to clear out
some of his stuff
while she's away
at bartending training.
Oh. LaDonna and I found
a torn page amongst his things.
I'm seeking the rest of it.
I could help you
sort through everything.
Yeah, of course.So...
Claudette doesn't mind you
going to her apartment
while she's away?
Mind your business.
She's finally down.
Thanks, Mrs. G.
You've been working
a lot of long hours lately.
Yeah.
You could afford help
around your house.
But Mariah loves you.
She barely lets me
put her down anymore.
Logan, I'm an old lady.
I got simple pleasures.
I can't enjoy all of them
when I'm taking care of a baby.
And, somehow, I got myself
into taking care of a man
without any of the benefits.
Now, I love y'all,
but I'm not a crutch
you can lean on forever.
We can't go on like this.
And this bed
is pretty uncomfortable.
It's okay for you
to never forget Shanice,
but you got to move on.
You should talk to somebody.
Ah, I don't know.
Talking to somebody
about this feels...
It makes it real?
Baby, it is real.
Even if she did come back,
you can't pick up
where you left off.
So...
you're getting up out of
this bed, so help me.
If not therapy,
I'm signing you up
for FOMO-Mates.
Oh, no.
Okay. Point taken.
Shanice was like
a daughter to me,
but she's not here.
She's not even in that
big old empty house
that you won't go home to.
You've got to accept the truth.
Bury what you can,
and live with the rest.
My sister was a lot
of things to a lot of people.
To me, she was everything.
It's been five years
since I...
we lost her,
but, uh...
why can't I move on?
Why am I still acting out and...
God, making the worst decisions.
Me and my girlfriend, uh...
Me...
and my ex-girlfriend
just recently broke up,
and, uh, not even
a second later I'm
hooking up with a co-worker.
Still trying to make it
all make sense.
I'm still pretty new here,
so, uh, thanks
for, uh,
letting me share.
Thank you for sharing.
I know it's hard.
Yeah, thank you.
I, uh...
see a couple new faces, so, uh,
guess I got to do
introductions, right?
Hi. I'm Logan.
Hi, Logan.
I've been away a while 'cause
I thought I had it handled.
Oh, yeah.
Guess not.
So, back in Grief Group.
A while back,
the love of my life,
this brilliant,
hard-ass lawyer
married me.
You know, we had a family
and everything.
It was-it was kind of perfect,
to be honest.
Then she up and vanished.
I wa-I was frantic.
I-I was worried something
terrible had happened to her.
I just hoped that
I could find her,
save her.
Well...
Then, uh,
they found this letter.
Police gave me this letter.
You know, I-I don't know
what destroyed me more,
The thought of losing her or...
the idea that...
maybe she was out of my life
because that's what she wanted.
Even so,
I looked for her for years.
Then she came back.
Not because she had
a change of heart or anything,
she just literally came back.
She fell out of the sky
and landed on my doorstep.
Wait. She's a 4,400?
Look, I-I-I...
This is a grief group,
not a 4,400 support group.
You got what everybody here
prays for,
and you want our sympathy?
That's what this
is about... 4,400?
Somebody's playing you, man.
The whole thing's a hoax.
A hoax? A hoax.
No. That is not what this is.
It is real, There's no way that people
are falling out of the sky.
And it is a gift from God. No,
I don't think you understand...
How do you not have any hope?
Hello?
Logan?
You answered.
Shanice. You've been calling?
Right, right, yes.
I wanted to invite you, um...
to be a part of...
this thing with me.
Y-You mean this
Meet the 4,400 thing?
Yeah, yeah.
It's-it's a way for the,
for the world to kind of...
you know, get to know us.
It's not just you.
Mariah, Hayden... Bridget.
It would be all of us together,
kind of showing how we're
one big, happy family.
Is that what we are?
What do you want with me?
I'll think about the event.
But...
it's a lot right now, okay?
Okay.
Yeah. Fine.
Is everything okay? That sounded
like an intense call.Yeah. It was
just Shanice.
She wants me to be a part
of this Meet the 4,400 event.
Yeah, Jharrel
mentioned something
about you all
appearing together, or... Yeah.
It's not that
I don't want to help.
I would love to tell the world
how great it's been having
Hayden as a part of my family,
but... Shanice.
The man I heard in group...
The one struggling
with Shanice coming back...
He spoke with love.
That "against all odds"
kind of love,
and the closest thing
I have to that is my sister.
I'm here because I have
all of this love for her
that I don't know
what to do with.
And I'd give anything
to talk to her one last time.
I'm sorry about your sister.
Now, you heard them.
You have been given
the second chance
that so many people
in that group...
Myself included...
Are jealous of.
It's not that simple.
Oh, in some ways, it is.
Well, I hope something
in here helps.
You, uh, certainly know your
way around Claudette's home.
It's almost as if you spend
quite a bit of time here.
What did I tell you
about minding your own business?
Oh, yes,
me and Claudette hooked up
a little while back,
and we've just been
I don't... enjoying the vibes,
seeing where things go.
Is that how dating works now?
No declarations, just... vibes?
Depends.
Well, I'm asking because.
Shanice and I have been...
enjoying vibes as well,
but, yesterday Logan stopped by,
and...
watching them together...
How do I compete
with romantic history
when I don't know
the first thing about
21st century courtship?
Listen.
Given that I ruined
my last relationship
with Carla because
I was too obsessed with finding
my missing brother, Manny, I...
don't really have
a lot of advice to give,
but you...
Okay, I mean,
you do know that Shanice
is kind of a situation, right?
I mean, you sure
you can handle that?
Well, if I catch your meaning,
Claudette qualifies
in that category as well.
Are you sure you can handle her?
Touché.
Wait, is that it?
Okay, so what is that? It's
the rest of the COBOL code.
You think it has something to do
with what happened to you all?
I'll admit, we are working
on conjecture,
but the way your brother
disappeared like us...
You thought you saw
a green light.
Yeah, but I don't know.
That's why this might be
a fruitless search, but
we desperately need answers,
anything that can help us
get out from
the government's clutches.
Yeah, I hear you on that.
But if Manny is somehow
related to all of this, I...
I hope we can find answers that
will bring us all some peace.
Did Logan ever tell you
if he's coming?
Nope.
Carla's busy figuring out
some other family
for the segment.
If he's upset about... About us?
Do you think he might be?
I-I don't know.
After all this is through,
I request your presence
in the cocktail lounge,
to celebrate your successes.
Andre, that's not necessary. Oh, it is.
I'm handling my situation.
I know how hard you've worked
to make sure this event
helps us all,
even those of us who signed
a terrible contract.
It is appreciated.
That man... was at Ypsi Med.
I remember he had flames
dancing up his arms.
Does that mean
they're releasing patients?
Do you think Noah could be next?
You said that man's power
is fire?
LaDonna assured me all
our powers are "fire."
But in all seriousness,
what are you thinking?
I don't know,
it could be nothing.
I'll find you later. Promise.
Just got out of
a security briefing.
First thing they do is
shove a tranq in our hands.
Why would they up security
for interviews?
And more importantly, who are
those even supposed to protect?
Jharrel... Oh, Shanice.
I think Bill Greene
is up to something.
He brought in a 4,400
from Ypsi Med
whose power is apparently
shooting flames from his arms.
Okay, wait, the 4,400 he added
to the interview list
last second?
And it sure looked like the
Reverend was in on it with him.
I knew I couldn't trust him.
He'd be fine
revealing the powers.
He practically did it with
Ji-Eun at his last event.
I think he wants it out
in the world.
Wait a minute, you think
that's what the government's
trying to do here;
Expose y'all's powers?
But why would they do that?
Because our powers could be
exactly what they need
to trigger the conservatorships.
All of a sudden,
the world thinks
we need to be looked after.
That we need
to be taken care of.
We can't let that happen.
Why is that man here
from Ypsi Med?
Are you and the government
trying to
reveal our powers to the world?
You could be putting us all
in danger.
You only see me as a threat,
don't you?
Did it ever occur to you
that I'm trying to do right
by our people?
You aren't the only one
who knows how to
make a difference, Shanice.
Jharrel, he's in here.
What is this all about?
Hey, man, did they
give you any orders?
I show them what I can do.
Brûler...
Then they set me free.
Anything is better than
going back to where they kept me.
Okay.
Shanice was right.
We got to make sure
they don't have any other
tricks up their sleeve...
Is it smart, leaving him here?
Look, we're trying
to protect you.
Get everybody out
from underneath
the government's thumb.
Ca... Can you trust us?
I want us all to be free.
Us, too.
Stay here until we get you.
Hello to everyone at home.
This is Gladys Keller.
Today, we're bringing you
an in-depth special
on the mysterious 4,400.
Are they just like us, victims
of some terrible circumstance,
or is there more to the story?
We're pulling back the curtain,
and hearing from them
in their own words,
live and unedited.
Our first guest,
the prestigious
Reverend Isaiah Johnston,
declared deceased in 1993,
brings us to the heart of it.
Thank you for that introduction.
As for your question,
I don't think there is
a difference between
the 4,400 and everyone else.
See, the Lord works
in mysterious ways.
We don't know why
we were brought here,
but we're all human, Gladys.
I'm curious, and I'm sure
the folks at home are, too.
Why are you all
under the protection
of the U.S. government?
The government is simply
doing right
by a vulnerable population.
Something I think we'd all
want them to do more of.
Wouldn't you, Gladys?
Shanice is right this way.
I'm so glad you all
could make it.
Hey, Shanice.Hi.
I know it'll be
a little strange for us all
to share the stage together
and act like...
well, um...
And it's probably the last thing
you want to do,
especially with
your vacation coming up.
Are you excited?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Uh, Mom... Yes?
Um, I think they want us to
get mics put on or something.
Come on.
We'll see you out there. All right.
Okay. Come on.
Can we talk somewhere,
in private, maybe?
Is everything okay?
Are you upset about
seeing me with Andre?
I don't know what
the rules are here. I know.
You're married
to someone else now,
and I just thought you didn't
want anything to do with me.
Am I being unfaithful?
No. You're not.
I am.
Look, right or wrong, I was
upset seeing you with Andre.
It's hard not to have
these feelings
when you're the first woman
I ever fell in love with.
And when you left,
it-it broke me.
I still don't know how
I picked up the pieces.
That's not true.
'Cause a part of me never did.
I've been waiting and hoping
for all that it's worth
that you'd come back one day.
Are you saying you want
to give us a second chance?
I'm sorry.
It's taken me till now
to realize we...
we can't go back.
There's no erasing
the last 16 years.
When you came back,
we got our second chance,
but it was a second
chance at closure.
I don't understand.
No, no, I know that
I was supposed to come onstage
and-and talk about
our happy, blended,
non-traditional family,
but I can't do that with you
anymore, Shanice.
I've got to make
a clean break and move on.
I've got to commit
to my family, to Hayden.
This...
It's not fair to us
or the people who love us.
We are good people, Shanice.
It's time we deal with reality.
One reality being that
you're still gonna be
a kick-ass mom to Mariah.
I want that for both of you...
even if I can't be
a part of it.
This is goodbye, Shanice.
Just-just wait.
You can't close
the investigation.
No, you're asking me
to give up hope on my wife,
and I won't. She wouldn't
give up on me. I'm sorry,
but she made it pretty clear
she doesn't want to be found.
What?
What are you talking about?
You've gotta let me go, Shanice.
I know.
You should go
be with your family.
Thank you.
And we are back, live
from the Bois Blanc Hotel.
I'm happy to introduce you
to the first truly blended
4,400 and 2021 family.
We have husband and wife Logan
Kaminski and Bridget Templeton,
their beautiful daughter
Mariah, and Hayden Turner,
the 4,400 they've welcomed into
their home. Hello, everyone.
Thanks, Gladys.
We're just so happy
to have been able
to invite Hayden into our home.
It's really been wonderful.
Hey, Rev.
Sister Shanice.
Aren't you supposed to be
up there with your family?
Don't tell me you got
dressed up for nothing.
Nope. It all worked out
how it was supposed to.
Thank you for doing
the right thing.
I think the government wanted
to make a spectacle out of us
on live television so they could
control us further.
The right thing would be
letting Bill Greene know
what I think about those
contracts he made people sign.
I looked into it after
we spoke the other day.
I should have realized
what he was up to.
Hubris on my part.
But make no mistake.
I won't let anyone
harm these people.
Is it true that, along with
sponsoring Hayden, your wife...
Well, ex-wife... Shanice
is also one of the 4,400?
For years, we...
we wondered what happened.
I don't think we ever could have
imagined the truth, though.
It freed me in some ways.
Now, obviously, there...
There are bigger mysteries
to be solved,
but I'm blessed to have gotten
a closure that few get.
You know, a new lease on life
that I'm just very grateful
to have.
Our fire starter is
somehow AWOL.
We have people trying
to look for him,
but what are we supposed to do?
We have names.
Mildred.
So glad you're safe.
I'm not safe.
None of us are safe.
Having Hayden come into
our home was unexpected,
but he's brought so much good
into our lives, I can't imagine
him being anywhere else.Yeah.
And how about you, Hayden?
Are you happy?
More than I thought I could be.
I understand you're upset.
But believe it or not, we have
been very worried about you.
So has your sister Millicent.
Here's what I want.
You free them,
and I'll let you go.
All it takes is one call.
Well, after this broadcast,
you may be the first
4,400 heartthrob, Hayden.
He's taken.
No, not by me. Another 4,400.
She's like, so awesome.
Stop lying.
The government doesn't
care about us.
We're just experiments to you.
But you guys forget that
we're the ones who have power.
I can take you to your sister.
She's been quite upset
since you left.
Mildred.
Oh, my God.
Mildred?
Let's go.
Go. Go, go, go.
Up. Up in the window.
Mildred, you have to stop this.
This isn't the plan
God chose for us.
You kept me a prisoner
for no reason.
Well, I'll give you a reason.
No.
Stop.
Fine! You're next.
What did you do to my powers?
What did you do to me?
I... I don't know.
But you can't let them
catch you.
Run. Run!
There's an exit this way.
Please move safely.
No. No. Excuse me. Excuse me.
Keisha. Keisha.
I need your help.
Bridget and Mariah are safe, but
I can't find Hayden anywhere.
I-I might know where he is.
Wait. Did you know
about their powers?
I knew about the powers.
Okay? But what just
happened with Mildred,
that I had no idea
was gonna happen.
Does-does Hayden? Can he...
You gotta let him tell
you in his own way.
The whole world saw that,
Keisha. It was live.
I mean, what's gonna
happen to them?
I don't know.
I don't know. Come on.
Excuse me.
Well, I'll give you a reason.
Look, you can just
pack up my stuff
and just drop it off
at the hotel, okay?
I know you don't want me
in your home anymore.
Now that you know
I've been lying to you.
I'm not mad at you.
I'm upset with the adults
who kept things from me,
but, Hayden...
you're just a kid
dealing with an
impossible situation.
It's my job to protect you.
I am not going anywhere.
I saw how much you
cared about Mildred
when you broke her
out of Ypsi Med.
Must have been hard
seeing her like that.
This is all my fault.
Isn't it?
I messed up.
I should have helped her.
I should have known...
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Come here.
Sometimes loving someone
isn't enough to save them...
or your relationship with them.
But that does not mean...
that you aren't enough.
That you didn't give it
everything you've got.
It just means...
you had different roads
to go down.
Okay?
You ready to come home now?
Aren't you afraid
of what my power is?
I know you'd never hurt us.
I don't need to know
your power to know that.
You can tell me
when you're ready.
I just want you safe.
Welcome to Harlem, 1924.
Seeing it in my memories
is no replacement
for seeing it in the... flesh.
What is wrong?
The event went terribly, Andre.
Mildred was there.
She threw Bill Greene
out the window.
The powers are out
for the world to see.
Oh, no...
I think the conservatorships
are gonna be triggered.
Your conservatorship.
I'm terrified of what is
gonna happen to you.
As am I.
I am terrified for all of us.
And that is a problem
we will have to face tomorrow.
But for now, we dance like
tomorrow will never come.
We have to figure out
how to protect you.
Tomorrow.
Captioning sponsored by CBS.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org