Shanice, it's time to wake up.
Are we in Paris?
Yeah.
I just picked up
some croissants for breakfast.
Fresh ones.
And are we gonna stroll
by the Seine later
and make out on a
bridge at sunset?
Definitely.
Liar.
Not about - the making out part.
Okay. All right, Mariah.
Hi.
You are gonna be
in so much trouble
if you didn't bring her
a croissant.
Don't you have somewhere to be?
Yes.
Yes, it's a bad look for me
to be late on my first day back.
Especially when
Mr. Zimmer
has it out for me.
Oh, no. No, you've kept up
with everything
during maternity leave.
You're gonna be back
and better than ever.
- Right?
- That's right.
Just got to face
the day in front of me.
That's perfect.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
All right.
- Ah. BlackBerry.
- There you go.
- All right.
- Come on.
- I got you.
- Yeah.
Have a nice day.
- Okay. I love you.
- I love you. Mwah.
Bye.
If you ready to move.
What is this?
I don't know, but it won't stop.
Pardon me!
What in heaven's name?
What is this?
Where am I?
I-I think...
I think it's Belle Isle?
Is that... Is
that in Brooklyn?
No. Detroit.
I-I'm a physician.
I should...
Wait.
Sirens? An air raid?
I...
Keisha Taylor.
Are you social work
or corrections?
I'm a parole officer.
Can someone tell me
what all this is about?
You'll be briefed
and assigned a facility.
Okay, well, I'd like
to be briefed now.
Why don't you
go find some... Agent Tanner
with DHS. It's all right.
She's with me.
Okay, what's going on?
I show up to work today,
and my boss
tells me to report here.
Did... Did you do this?
Look, I know you've been saying
you want to get more serious,
but...
Did I go behind my
girlfriend's back
to try and coerce her
into working with me?
No.
I like how devoted you are
to your job.
In fact, your boss
recommended you.
Okay, for what?
Wh-What is all this?
You'll get a formal briefing,
but you saw the news about
those people on Belle Isle?
Yeah, some kind of protest.
Got out of hand.
That's the story we're
letting the press run with,
but there is zero chatter
or online organizing.
Thousands of people
just showed up.
We've tried fingerprinting
and run facial recognition
on hundreds so far.
The ones we've identified
are all missing persons cases
from the last couple decades.
Okay, so, what, they're all,
like, kidnapped and returned?
Unlikely.
They're from all
over the country.
All over the world.
- Some don't even speak English.
- Okay, Jessica,
what you are talking about is...
I know.
We're putting together teams
of corrections officers
and social workers
to see if you can get some
information out of them.
Quickly.
We've just been battling this
on all fronts,
especially trying
to keep it out of the press
until we have any kind
of handle on it.
Well, in my experience,
people lie when they get caught
doing things
they aren't supposed to.
We'll find the truth.
Can you tell me
what you remember?
Okay,
we're gonna figure this out.
We're gonna get everything
back to normal.
- I-I swear I'm gonna - do whatever I can do.
- Let me take a look at this.
Yes. It's not as bad
as I thought.
You doing all right, miss?
You know anything
about all this?
Was gonna ask you the same.
Well, last I knew,
I was in Mississippi,
and-and now they saying
we in Detroit?
This how people dress
in Detroit? How they act?
Something doesn't add up.
I'm Reverend Johnston. Isaiah.
It's a pleasure to meet you...
Little young to be a reverend,
aren't you?
Inherited the position.
Jesus is our family business.
Well, hopefully Jesus can
provide you with some insight.
If you'll excuse me.
Hi. I don't know
what kind of prank
my friends are pulling,
but I'm done.
Oh, um, this isn't actually...
Yeah, I mean,
this is all, like, real.
No. No.
Like, people must be looking
for me.
Okay, I have to get out of here
and tell my dad
I'm okay, so just...
Give me my phone back
and get me out
of this janky-ass hotel.
I need to speak with
whoever is in charge.
We have rights. You can't just
keep us here without cause.
Uh, sorry, everyone,
we can't actually...
I need to speak
with whomever is in charge
of medical personnel.
I need supplies.
- A workspace.
- We're not gonna get anything
while they continue to hold us
as prisoners.
Isn't that right?
I am with
a very prestigious law firm,
and I am going to rain hell down
on everyone who is party
to this unlawful detention.
Madam, I don't think
that kind of language
is constructive,
and I'm not sure
a secretary is
the most convincing messenger.
Excuse me?
You did not just say that
in Ruth Bader Ginsburg's
America.
Aw, sad.
RIP RBG, am I right?
What do you mean, "RIP"?
Well, like, how she died
last year?
It was pretty big news.
If...
If Justice Ginsburg had died,
I think I would have
heard about it.
Ruth Bader Ginsburg,
the new Supreme Court justice?
Apologies, whom
are we discussing?
Ruth Baiter...? There aren't any women
on the Supreme Court.
Can you just imagine?
I don't understand why
we're talking about...
or still talking
about the Supreme Court.
- Wait.
- There are things
that we need right here,
right now, like... Wait a minute.
Wait!
What-what year is it?
Um, it's-it's 2021.
- Where are the cameras?
- Did you say 2021?
Where are the cameras?
Are you serious?
Yeah, what year did
you guys think it was?
This must be a mistake.
How can that be?
I can't be in 2021.
That would just be...
I don't know.
Hey. You must be Keisha.
I'm Jharrel.
Social worker. Heard
we're gonna be partners.
This whole thing is wild, huh?
Excuse me. The
plexiglass should remain
for the duration
of the interviews.
I might have asked them
to take those down.
Look, I know they ran us through
the whole quarantine protocol,
but I work with immigrants
and refugees every day,
and trust me,
it is hard to connect
- with people through - suits and walls.
- Jharrel, is it?
I understand
you're the people person,
and I respect that, but this
is a volatile situation.
The rules are in place
for a reason.
Let's not break them on day one
just 'cause we want to get
in our feelings, okay?
- Glass stays on the table.
- Yes, ma'am.
Why didn't you
come to me sooner?
I noticed
your difficulty walking.
For all I know,
you just some charlatan
playing doctor.
Besides, I'm...
I'm well-accustomed to pain.
Well, I can put your mind
at ease that I am no charlatan.
I spend my time
running a clinic
up in North Harlem...
Hmm... where I get
to treat lots of ornery
Black folk like yourself.
You need to be seen.
There's white folk in here, too.
You would think...
Mm-hmm. All this talk
about the future.
You know, my husband and I
have been jailed and worse
for organizing the vote
for Negroes.
If it was really 2021,
I'd have hoped
we'd made more progress.
That it wouldn't feel the same.
I was driving to work.
My first day back
after maternity leave.
And then suddenly,
there was this,
like, wind.
And I saw a green light
out of my window,
and then everything went black.
Wait, wait, I'm sorry.
You said you saw a light?
Like, a green light?
Yeah.
And now 16 years have passed?
I'm not lying.
I'm speaking without counsel
because something strange
happened.
I've cooperated,
and you all have told me nothing
about what I'm being accused of.
- We're trying to get - to the truth.
- The truth is
that I just want to go home.
Please, my-my daughter, Mariah,
she's only four months old.
I hear you. All
right, and we are
working as fast as we can
to figure this out.
All right, we have a
bunch of people working
across the dozens of facilities
that are housing all of you.
Oh, my God,
that could take days.
Weeks.
And you're not gonna let me
see them, are you?
Bathroom's down the
end of the hall.
They're giving everybody
ten minutes, okay?
You okay?
No.
Oh, okay.
I've never been apart
from my baby
for more than a few hours.
She must be so scared.
I'm Shanice, by the way.
Mildred.
And I'm sorry.
You seem like a good mom.
I just want to get back to her.
What is going on?
I don't know,
but you should go.
- Yes, we should. Come on.
- I'm okay here.
I have nowhere to go.
Go to your family
and your baby. I'll stay here.
I'll keep watch.
I'll see you again
when I get you out of here,
okay?
Next stop, Woodward
and the Detroit Institute
of Arts.
That's just my baby dog.
No blood for oil!
Louder!
- No blood for oil!
- All right, let's go. You got to move.
No blood for oil!
- What?!
- No blood for oil!
You got to move. - You're blocking the sidewalk.
We have the right to... No blood for oil!
No blood for oil!
- Hey! Hey, - don't put your hands on her!
- No blood for oil!
- She was pushed. - You could see that.
No blood for oil!
- No blood for oil!
- Watch yourselves.
No blood for oil!
- No blood for oil!
- You all right?
Oh, I'm fine.
It's that man
who wasn't raised right!
I know, right?
I don't know how parents
let their kids go out
in the world and treat
people like that.
This seems to be a pattern among
people who look a lot like you.
Fair.
Well, I'm gonna make
sure that my kid
has a kick-ass mom
who organizes protests
against travesties
like this sham war.
- No blood for oil!
- You got us raising kids
- before you even - bought me coffee?
- No blood for oil!
- Yeah, sorry.
- No blood for oil! No blood for oil!
Hey, I'm Logan, by the way.
You want to get coffee?
I'm a little busy right now.
And I'm not really trying
to discuss kids.
That's a long ways off for me.
That right?
That's right.
I am getting my law degree,
and I'm gonna advocate
for the people in my community
who have been screwed over
more times than I can count.
Detroit is on the verge
of a comeback,
and I plan to be a part
of making it happen.
All that's pretty heavy
for coffee.
I didn't say I'd go... It's
definitely first dinner talk, though.
- You free tonight?
- No blood for oil!
No blood for oil!
No blood for oil! No blood
for oil! No blood for oil!
We've interviewed 15 people
so far and gotten nowhere.
Well, we know that
they all cleared
their medical screenings.
They don't pose a
danger to anyone.
But we don't know that.
Are we supposed to believe
these people don't remember
- anything -about what happened to them?
- Keisha,
they're just as confused
as we are.
All right? We should help them.
Tell the public,
alert family members.
Tell the public what?
Some people got snatched up
by a green light
and just showed back up
out of nowhere? No.
There's something we're missing.
Okay, and how long
until we have answers?
In the meantime, we are leaving
a lot of people out there
believing that their loved
ones are never coming home
when, really, we got them
locked up here in this hotel.
Have a seat.
Hey, I have to run an errand
real quick.
Can you take the last interview
of the day for me? Thanks.
You haven't spoken a word
since you arrived, huh?
I will need to find
new bandages.
This is remarkable.
It's almost fully healed.
How did this happen?
Did you receive treatment
from their doctors?
No, I didn't.
I-I think I should... Oh, no.
No, I'm fine.
It mustn't have been so
bad after all.
Go on, now. You got other
patients who need you.
Do you know sign language?
- What's going on?
- We have a problem.
Shanice Murray escaped.
I bet she's heading home.
Logan?
Logan, it's me.
Come on. Come on.
Logan!
Logan, please come out!
Someone's
breaking into my house.
She's Black.
Yes, I think she's armed.
You got here fast.
- Oh, he's with me.
- I got your text.
Owner just called the cops.
We're gonna fan out.
She's close.
And she's got no place
to stay. Cold night.
She'll find a place
that's open late.
Warm up.
Look, I think I saw a
diner down the street.
Hey.
Where do you think you're going?
Like he said, let's fan out.
Who is it?
It's-it's Shanice.
It's Shanice Murray.
Haven't known anybody
by that name in a long while.
Mrs. Grover,
you-you changed my diapers,
did my hair and fed me
every day after school.
Plus, I know that shotgun's
about a hundred years old,
and you're gonna hurt yourself
if you try to shoot me.
Neecey?
That you?
Come on in here out of the cold.
You're gonna
catch your death.
Jasmin. Hey.
Look, any sign of Manny at the
facility you were assigned to?
All right, hit me up
if you find anything.
Thanks.
They say this is
like a soda pop?
You just poke a hole in it?
Guess the government couldn't
spring for the real thing.
You pull the tab
on the top. Here.
Well, I'll be.
It's all bubbly
like just from the fountain.
Yes, ma'am.
Keep the line moving.
Let's go.
I told them I am
a sometime pescatarian,
ovo vegetarian.
Like, what is so
complicated about that?
Oh, my God.
Do you even speak English?
I have called home,
his office, his cell phone.
All disconnected.
How am I gonna track them down?
I couldn't find
your-your phone book.
The city stopped
putting those out years ago.
- Oh, my gosh.
- But I wrote down
the new address when they
moved out to Palmer Woods.
- Palmer Woods?
- Mm-hmm.
What's the address?
Can I borrow the Pontiac?
The car is gone.
And there is not
much more you can do
- until you get some sleep.
- No, I have to...
You're dead on your feet.
You're talking nonsense
and don't even know it.
Come on, now.
Drink your Vernors.
Rest up,
and you can find your
husband in the morning.
A few more hours ain't
gonna change anything
now that you're back.
I'm glad to see
you're not too much
like your daddy after all.
I'm nothing like him.
I didn't leave.
I...
I don't know what happened.
I wa...
I was home yesterday.
I just want to close my eyes
and have everything return
to normal.
I mean, if I... if...
If I can just see Logan
and-and...
and hug my little baby...
It'll be okay.
I know it will.
It has to be.
Well, damn. Lurk much?
Can I help you?
Yes. Yes. I want you to cut me.
Oh, my God.
Um, lady, look,
I know this is all a hot mess,
but are you okay?
They won't give us
anything sharp,
so I need to use your nails.
Absolutely not.
Do you have any idea
how much I paid for these?
I just want to test a theory.
Do it, and I won't tell
that guard you're sweet on
that you just made
yourself sick in here.
That's none of your business.
No, it surely isn't.
Fine.
Oh, my God.
Well, thank you kindly,
and you have a nice day now,
you hear?
I'm sorry, wait a minute.
That's it?
I mean, like, you're not gonna
bleed out, are you?
'Cause I am not trying to go
down for murder in a bathroom,
so... I...
Madam. Mrs. Williams,
you mustn't...
But how can that be?
Is this some medical advance
from this era?
Nope, because I tried it,
and it still stings.
But-but hers healed up
even faster this time.
I don't know how to explain it,
but I just started
feeling better.
Gradually more and more,
a-and now...
Now I feel great.
Well, that makes one of us.
I think...
I think this could be
very detrimental to you
and perhaps to all of us
if they found out
about this.
We should not tell anyone else.
As if.
You know what? I don't know
what you two weirdos
are talking about,
and I don't care.
I'm so over all this.
I'm not going back.
Do you understand?
You can't keep me
from them. You have
- no legal right.
- Whoa, hey, hey.
I agree.
I don't like the way this thing
is being run, either.
But I'm not the one in charge.
So...
I'll take you to
see your family.
Look, I'll work it out
with the agents who are
watching the door to
your husband's house.
But you got to return to the
hotel with me afterwards.
Deal?
Why would you help me?
Because if I was your family,
I would give anything
to know that you were okay.
Okay.
This is me.
Weren't you
wearing that yesterday?
Guilty.
But you definitely
weren't wearing that.
Hey, Mrs. Grover's
sense of fashion is timeless.
Just ask her.
Let us out!
Let us out! Let us out!
Let us out! Need some
backup in the lobby.
Everybody's so stressed out.
- Let us out!
- Back up. Back up!
- You are in the custody
- of the United States government.
- Let us out!
You are being housed and
fed with our tax dollars.
- You all need to - stand down now!
- Let us out!
Let us out! Let us out!
Let us out!
Let... Okay! O-Okay, folks.
I know it's been a long
couple of days, and tensions
are high. I feel you
on that, all right?
Now, we know it ain't right
to keep us locked up
when we haven't done
anything wrong.
But we also know that
something strange is going on
because just a couple days ago,
I was kicking back
watching Jordan
lead the Bulls
in the NBA Finals.
Hector, you had just gotten
back from the Korean War.
And, LaDonna, you were out
at some party. Then suddenly,
- you're here.
- So unfair.
The government's trying to help.
And I think maybe they can find
a way to show us that.
How about we open up
some of those rooms
for people to have
- a real bed to stay in tonight?
Those floors
- are currently closed.
- We have some time before nightfall.
As a gesture.
And tomorrow,
we'll be getting some answers.
That sounds like
a sign of good will to me.
For once.
That's right. We're all trying
to do our best here.
We're blessed in that.
Amen.
That was well-done
of the reverend.
That's because he
knows how to use
pretty words
to make people believe him.
Men like him?
They dangerous.
Why would you think that?
Because I'm married to one.
Mariah?
You're...
Mom?
Oh, my God.
It's really you.
You're...
You're really...
You're grown
Mariah, who's at
the door, sweetheart?
Logan?
Oh, thank God.
Shanice?
- Hey, get inside.
- But-but, Dad, wait.
- No, no, please.
- Come on. Come on, all right?
I can't believe it's her.
Um, look, I don't...
I don't have much time,
but I had to come
and-and see you.
What are you doing
here, Shanice?
I came to find you.
You wouldn't believe
what I have been through.
I mean,
I-I don't believe it, really,
but Mariah's a teenager,
so... Do you... Do you
really think
that you can just walk
out on your family
and come waltzing
back 16 years later
like it never happened?
"Walk out"?
That-That's not what happened.
I was taken
or-or something.
I don't actually know.
Wait, who's that?
He's... It's a long story.
That's what I'm trying
to tell you. The...
The day you say I left, for me,
that was two days
ago. I don't know.
I thought I'd have more time.
Logan, please, I need you
to listen to me.
I need help. We-we all
need help. They're
keeping us in this...
- in this hotel downtown.
- Wait, who? Who?
There was this agent... Sir, stand back.
This woman is
a national security threat.
She could pose a danger - to you and your family.
- That's not true.
- Mariah, stay back.
- What is going on?
Oh, my God.
Shanice?
You look just like
your pictures.
Shanice, you have
to come with us now.
How long?
Nine years.
And she, she...
She raised my daughter?
- Hey. Hey, hang on.
- No.
Don't put your hands on her.
I don't...
I don't know what you thought,
but I did not leave.
I would never have left you.
I love you.
You are my family, and I will do
everything I can
to get back to you
- and make you understand.
- I don't know what you got yourself into,
Shanice, but don't lie to me.
Don't lie to our daughter.
I found your note.
No. No, Logan.
That's not what you think.
I can explain, Logan!
Logan! I can explain!
That's not
what you think, Logan!
Logan!
Do you have any idea
the destruction you
caused that family?
Why?
I didn't put her
in this position.
You did. Okay? She was never
- supposed to make contact.
- She was coming in.
Quietly. But instead,
you traumatize the kid,
had to witness her mom
being treated like that.
Someone helped her escape.
- What, you think I did that?
- I don't know.
But I do know when people
have something to hide.
Yeah?
Well, you're a cop
who believes in the system
over people's humanity.
I don't really trust you,
either.
Mrs. Murray,
you look unwell.
Where have you been?
Are you all right?
Not really, Doc.
My husband...
is now married to someone else
who also raised
my 16-year-old daughter.
I...
I was so scared
when I got pregnant.
I wasn't ready to be a mother.
I had so much to do.
And when she was born,
it wasn't that immediate
connection they tell you
it's gonna be.
I was so worried
about my life changing,
about my career.
And she was this...
this strange, little creature.
I was in pain.
My head wasn't on straight.
But I got help.
And she and I, we...
We grew into our love.
We fought
to get where we were, you know?
And I was never gonna stop
fighting for her.
But I missed it all.
Her first words.
Her first steps.
Her first everything.
She was this tiny, little blob
in my arms, and now she
has had a whole life.
And...
she didn't...
she didn't need me.
You're gonna get to sleep
in a real bed tonight.
I thought at least that would've
put a smile on your face.
No.
No, I'm in the future,
and you're, like,
one of the X-Men.
- I'm a what now?
- And I'm stuck in this dump,
I'm totally alone,
and I just want my phone back.
I'll admit I think y'all have
a real surprising attachment
to telephones now.
And
I can't say
what's happening here
other than to take as truth
what I done seen
with my own two eyes.
But I do know one thing.
You're not alone.
You, me, the doc,
everyone in here,
we are all in this together.
And that's the only way we gonna
get through it. You hear me?
Say, you think
that piano's in tune?
Old people are far-out.
Am I to ascertain that ragtime
is no longer in vogue?
Wait till you
hear the "Thong Song."
Mrs. Williams is
quite a surprising talent.
Perhaps she'll play it for us.
Maybe.
In the meantime,
would you care to dance?
Okay, they've had their fun.
You have to stop playing, ma'am.
- Hey, what is wrong with you?
- She tripped.
- I didn't touch her.
- Is there some rule
against playing the piano
that nobody knows about?
This isn't summer camp.
We have a schedule.
- Come on!
- Line up!
Rotating the second
shift into dinner
in five.
The piano is off-limits.
You okay?
- Let me see.
- I'll examine her,
but it looked benign to me.
Really? Because it sounded
like it was bad... Just-just
hit my funny bone is all.
But thank you for your concern.
This seat taken?
I'm not interested.
And I'm definitely
not interested.
Now, I have to turn in
a report tomorrow morning
about what went down today,
and...
Look, is there anything
you want to tell me?
A reason you're so protective
of Shanice Murray?
I was protective
because I have seen what happens
when a powerful
government machine
treats people like
they're problems
- instead of human beings.
- That's not what's happening.
Okay... We don't know
what's happening.
All right? We know some people
appeared out of nowhere,
and some of them
are from the past.
Now, tell me, how do you think
our government
is gonna react to that?
Look, you might
be a good person.
All right, the people we report
to might be good people.
But even good people
justify very bad things
in the name of doing their jobs.
In the name
of keeping people safe.
The truth is, I thought...
My brother Manny is missing,
and I thought that I had seen
a green light out the window
right after he left.
The first time
in a year
I had real hope.
There's no sign of Manny
among any of these people.
And I am gonna have to face
the fact
that I'll probably
never see him again.
Well, it's been real.
I'll fix it with DHS.
Okay? I've got...
connections.
So that is what is going on
between you and Agent Tanner,
huh? Connections.
I know what it's like
to lose someone
you were supposed to protect.
Okay, my sister was killed
walking home from the library
five years ago.
Gunfire. Not meant for her.
A parolee who shouldn't
have had access to a weapon.
Keisha, I'm sorry. I didn't...
It's hard
to let anyone get close.
Anyone you could ever let down
like that again.
Easier to protect strangers.
Uh, hey, can you
turn that up for me?
We are following up
on explosive allegations
about the mysterious gathering
on Belle Isle two nights ago.
A whistleblower tells us
a number of the people
have been identified
as missing persons
who all appeared
at the same location
for reasons unknown.
We are told the total number
of returnees
is 4,400,
and they're being held
at undisclosed locations.
Where'd you disappear
to yesterday?
- I got out.
- Out?
- How?
- I don't know.
The door just opened.
So that's what got
the guards' cages all rattled.
And?
Is it true?
Unless someone's put together
a very elaborate hoax,
it's really 2021.
And they came after me.
Sent the whole cavalry
to bring me back in.
That's a whole lot of effort
for one Black woman.
Yep. So, why us?
Far as I can tell,
we have nothing in common.
Not where we're from.
Not when we're from.
So why now? Why this?
For some reason, we're special.
As much as I wish I didn't have
anything to do with any of this,
I've realized that if we have
that kind of value,
it means one more thing.
Yeah, and what's that?
We're not powerless.
I think I might just like 2021.
There's news vans outside.
- You holding up?
- Hounded by the press,
the White House,
people who think
we have their loved ones.
These people,
the ones we can find data on,
follow no clear pattern.
They're just standard
missing persons cases.
Others match records that defy
every logical explanation.
The Pentagon
is exploring every theory.
They're reading in NASA.
Do they think this is
something extraterrestrial?
I know it sounds crazy,
but the time period
discrepancies?
Some people have reported
seeing green lights?
The way none of this makes sense
or is even possible?
I'm glad you're here.
And...
be careful with them.
What are you doing out here?
I'm glad they finally found you
something else to wear.
Heard they were gonna hit up
the Salvation Army.
You know,
my sister and I saw her
at Ford Field when we were kids.
She wanted to be
a rapper/mogul/collaborator
just like Missy.
You don't even know who that is,
do you?
Come on.
Let's get you in a room
so you can get some sleep.
Tell Jharrel
that Manny's all right.
And that he's sorry
for everything.