Well, it's actually.
Jharrel's apartment. I see.
And I suppose technically
it's his brother's. But the way
I'm finna look at it now
is it's my place,
- my space, my taste.
- Uh-huh.
Oh, uh, someone's at the door.
I better go.
Oh, Mrs. Grover,
please don't forget
about those newspaper clippings
you promised me.
Of course, dear.
I'll see you soon.
Jharrel.
Uh, come in.
Thanks. Hey,
I just...
Yo.
You really resuscitated
the place.
Feels like I'm
in the land of the living again.
To what do I owe this honor?
Well, I wanted
to, you know, check in.
See how you were doing.
I thought you're not
my case worker anymore.
That you're assigned to work
with the 4,400
coming into the hotel.
Although I'm not sure why
in Lord's name they'd want to
since we've been granted
our freedom.
Yeah, I guess they all
want to drink the Kool-Aid
Rev is serving.
You know they're
coming because of him.
And you came here for me?
What?
O-Oh, um, yeah.
No, I was just
in the neighborhood
and, um, you know, kind of
drove here automatically.
Habit.
Well, since you're here,
allow me to give you a tour
of my new digs.
Starting with my darkroom.
I'm taking up photography again.
Starting with all the
historic sites of Motor City.
So, I've been thinking.
Um, I refuse
to live only on this government
stipend like I did my husband.
Never know when the rug's gonna
get pulled out from under you.
Okay, hold up.
Did you say you want a J-O-B?
You know, I might actually be
able to help you out with that.
I got a guy.
Oh, you got a guy?
Do you now, Jimmy Hoffa?
Explain to me
how you thought it was okay
to allow my daughter
to be a getaway driver.
A getaway driver,
Andre! And then
fail to mention
that funny little fact
when you saw me.
You're sweating bullets.
Oh, best not get too close.
Indeed, I believe I am unwell.
- Well, let me get some help.
- No. Please.
I cannot risk being dragged off
to that dreadful institution.
In fact, I've not felt well
since I returned from Ypsi Med.
I'm sure it will pass.
Oh, my God, Andre.
You're in your pajamas.
Ew! Are you okay?
I'll be fine. I just need
a little rest is all.
Okay, cool, 'cause I
need to talk to you
about the files we
took from Ypsi Med.
I'm trying to figure
out how to read them,
and then you can
do your doctor-y
thing and figure out
- what the hell is - wrong with us.
- Okay,
you two,
to be continued.
And after I pick up some soup
and get you some electrolytes,
you and I are to be continued.
Thrilling.
Get back into that bed.
The U.S. government
will provide the 4,400
who stay at the Bois Blanc Hotel.
Meals. A stipend.
Free transportation.
- Clothes.
- Clothes?
What's the catch, Keisha? Mm.
Your guess is as good as mine.
All I know is
the government is
letting the 4,400 stay
at the Bois Blanc, but only
if they sign these contracts.
So, we give away our firstborn?
Well, you do, Shanice. Look,
this still might be better
than whatever my mom has planned
for me if I go back with her.
You're going home?
Who knows.
I can barely stand that woman
for more than one take,
let alone
- indefinitely.
- Look, I-I don't know
what's up with this contract.
What I do know is the government
hasn't said one word to us
since y'all heisted Ypsi Med.
- That's weird.
- Sus.
That's what we say nowadays,
lady from the aughts.
Y'all.
Right.
I'm gonna
go through the contract
and comb through the fine print.
On this thing, I guess?
- Don't even start.
- I did not say a word.
Look, you do you, boo.
I need to figure out
how to read these files
from Ypsi Med
on a very, very nongovernmental
computer. And you?
I've got to get to work.
Okay. Well, wonder triplets
unite or whatever.
It's-it's, like, what people
are doing nowadays, so just...
- No, they're not.
Okay. That is totally fine.
You guys are very vanilla.
Goodbye.
She's a mess.
Thank you.
Yeah.
No, sure. I got it.
I got it.
Okay, from the looks of it,
this doesn't seem that bad.
To the untrained eye, sure.
But we both have
very trained eyes
on how this government works,
which you and I
both know is sus.
Damn.
Soft on the 4,400.
Hard on the bosses.
Where did you lose your way?
Jharrel, shut up.
Wait, hold on.
Why are those people
being rushed?
Yeah,
that's the contracts booth.
Something's not right.
Yeah, I'll check in
with Shanice on what she found.
And tonight I'm having
dinner with Jessica.
Try and see what she knows.
A date with Jessica?
You better bring a sweater.
Boy, worry about
your own love life.
That's right, you don't got one.
Jharrel really
sang your praises.
How smart you are.
So, look, I know that barback
isn't the most glamorous...
Oh, I don't need glamour, sir.
Just a solid way to earn.
Barney.
This is Claudette.
Hi.
Nice to meet you.
See you around, newbie.
All right. Let's
get you started.
Forget it. Let's go.
Can I help you, ladies?
Can you get the Hulk's
attention over here?
Probably not.
Can you make us gin and tonics?
Y'all ever try a gin and sin?
Those cowards in hoods
bomb a church with our women,
our children
inside. What's next?
Jimmy will know what to do.
What a blessing that you
have a God-fearing husband
fighting for us,
organizing our sit-ins
- and such.
- Yes, truly blessed.
We sure do a lot of sitting.
Fighting, not so much.
- Good Lord, here she goes.
- Maybe it's time to fight.
- Fire with fire.
- Like Brother Malcolm. - I hear you,
Barb, I do. Maybe
just lower your voice a tad?
You took the photos, Claudette.
- Barb, shush.
- You saw the horrors up close.
- When you got back, - you were a mess.
- Barbara, lower
- your damn voice.
And with your photographs,
if you showed folks
the terror, the truth,
truth no set of eyes could deny,
they might be ready
to fight, too.
Everything all right over here?
- Just fine.
- Oh, peachy.
All right now, Jimmy?
Sir, help, please. I...
I need to find the ice machine
as I'm burning up.
Thought you were a doctor.
Can't you heal yourself?
Oh, dear God.
Oh, no.
How are they
supposed to understand this?
Andre? I thought you were sick.
I know you're cross with me,
but I don't know
who else to turn to.
Okay, Andre, you're scaring me.
I believe I possess a power.
Albeit a deadly one.
What?
Oh, my God.
Poor Tim.
Tim? The-the jerk guard
who took Hayden's chess set?
I touched him.
I held on to him for support,
and the poor fellow's
bones snapped.
I heard them break.
Then he lost his balance
and took a terrible tumble
down the staircase.
Oh, my God. Is-is he...?
Alive, yes.
Thank God.
This...
This all began at Ypsi Med.
I thought at first
I might be imagining it
amidst the adrenaline
and the chaos,
but now I think I actually...
healed the guard there.
Now, here's where
it seems
even more inconceivable.
Ever since then,
I have felt violently ill.
Until I broke Tim's bones.
Shanice,
a transference of sorts
must have taken place.
Okay.
You heal a person,
and then you ingest
some type of pain?
And the only way
to get rid of it
is to-to give it
to another person.
I took an oath to heal,
not harm.
I cannot risk hurting you.
We simply do not know the scope
of this power.
Hey. Sorry, - I didn't mean to scare you.
Um, I was
just waiting here because...
It's just that I...
Oh, my God. Words, LaDonna.
Spit it out.
I was just maybe hoping you
could help me out with a thing.
I already helped you, remember?
- Didn't turn out - so well for me.
- Yeah, I know, it...
It got, like, super emo.
But this is different.
I need help building
a computer from scratch.
That way,
there's absolutely no way
for the government
to access the files, okay?
No Internet, no Wi-Fi.
So the government
can't track it,
which keeps us both clean.
Look, I promise once
this ghost computer's built,
you're done.
We have to figure out
what we are
and what the hell
happened to us.
If you burn me,
you are dead to me.
- Again.
- Le duh.
You kind of had
me at "build a computer."
Oh, no, I am that geek.
This-this is the
moral of the story.
Do not listen to this man.
Cheers to that.
Claudette?
You know, our buddy Tim
is practically in a body cast.
Seems like one of you
did something to him
at the hotel.
- Wait, she didn't let you in.
- On her little secret. Bro,
- she's just trying to work.
Wait a minute.
You-You're one of them?
A 4,400?
Some are saying that your kind
might not even be human.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Going on break.
Congratulations,
Miss Independent!
Child. Get over here.
Oh, Mrs. G.
What is the matter?
I was a fool
to think I'd be allowed
to stand on my own two feet.
The date's changed, but...
some things stayed
exactly how they were.
Lord have mercy.
They gonna be ready
for the pamphlets?
Children died.
- What's next?
- As of today,
we got over a hundred folks
coming to the sit-in.
Not for the movement. For us.
When are they gonna stop
killing us?
I mean, they the damn ones
that brought us here
- only to hunt us for sport.
- Claudette, calm yourself.
I know you're upset...
We have tried the sit-ins
and the pamphlets.
When are we gonna go after them?
Our approach has been working,
and we will not stoop to
their level of depravity.
Trust me, woman, when I say
to you if we did,
things could get worse for us.
- What is worse - than this, James?
- Enough!
I let you do more
than you should.
More than what most husbands
let their wives do.
You should be grateful.
Now...
keep on taking your pictures
and leave the leading to me.
We clear?
Are we clear?
Yes, Jimmy.
So, will we finally be graced
with That LaDonna Life
if you leave the Bois Blanc?
I think I'm done
with reality TV.
But, like, all of a sudden,
my mom's inviting me home,
so who knows what that woman has
up her lipo garment sleeve.
I'd much rather go to my dad's.
Okay. Well, is that an option?
Not really.
I've tried
to get in contact with him,
but his number is unlisted.
Which I get. Like,
my mother literally cast him
as a villain on the show, so...
Oh, yeah. I remember.
She made him seem
like such a monster.
Well, he's not.
He was, like, the only person
to really get me, you know?
I used to be such a daddy's girl
before they split.
And then after he became
public enemy number one,
I couldn't see him as much.
My mom said
it wasn't a good look
for the show or whatever.
Oh, that's awful.
I'm sorry.
'Tis life.
But I can't stay here forever.
Oh, it's been really cool,
you know, like, learning to code
and using my brain and stuff,
but I do have a life back home.
My actual friends.
- Your friends from the show?
- Mm-hmm.
Girl, if those are your friends,
I would hate to
know your enemies.
They're not that bad.
They aren't. All right.
Saying goodbye to true friends
like you've made here?
I... You have told them,
- right?
- Okay, true friends? Like...
I've known these people
for, like,
half a season of television.
And no.
But it's my life.
They don't need to know.
Oh, honey.
You don't know
how to have friends.
It can be hard saying
goodbye to people.
Even if you've only known
the 4,400 for a short while.
Trauma bonds people.
Okay, that's not
what's happening here.
Okay? I'm too fabulous
for trauma.
Look, I just need to finish
this computer for them.
Besides that, nothing's
keeping me here, right?
Hey.
Ji-Eun, right?
Sorry,
I'm just checking up on folks.
Making sure you all got
what you need.
I noticed you
at the contracts booth.
You were asking for something.
A printout for my records.
The guy promised he would get it
by the end of the day.
- And still no copy?
- It's okay.
- I don't want to cause - any problems.
- No, hey, what problems?
It's your right to see them.
This man harassing you?
Just, uh, catching up
with one of your flock, Rev.
If that's allowed.
Ji-Eun,
remember what I told you.
If you need anything at all...
We have you.
Sure do. You ready
for prayer service?
Yeah.
I brought you what you
asked about the other day.
- The clippings?
- Mm-hmm.
Look at my girl.
"She went on
"to become a leader in
the Black Panther organization,
"believing,
'We stood by too many years,
"'hands behind our backs
to give them peace.
But we learned...'"
"'...only revolution
will guarantee the peace
Black folk deserve.'"
You know
what has changed?
In today's movement,
women's voices
are not only heard but followed.
Not as much as they should be,
but certainly more
than in your time.
I wonder what Barb
- would think of Barney.
- Yeah, Barb knew
there were a lot of Barneys
rotting this country
- from the inside out.
- What do you think
Barb would do if she knew
how high up the ladder
today's Barneys have climbed?
Sitting all high and mighty
in such powerful positions.
All right, listen up. Hey.
I have seen the photos of our
sisters and brothers up close.
Which is why
we are coming to
their front steps.
Yes! That's right.
We will bring our message
to the Klan's headquarters.
And sit like we always do?
Little sitting ducks
just waiting to be killed.
What if we make this personal
and strike
at the heart of the monster?
The Grand Wizard's house.
- Claudette.
- Yes, Claudette.
All right, dear.
That's enough.
Let her finish, Jimmy.
I'm not talking no sit-in.
We bomb
that white devil's house.
And nobody has to be there.
Nobody has to get hurt.
But we show him and his family
what it feels like
to be terrorized
and what we are capable of.
Attagirl. Yes!
It ain't a half bad idea.
Other organizations
have been striking back.
- Exactly.
- Yes.
- Heard there's been some success.
- There has.
There has, Jimmy.
Y'all have to excuse
my passionate wife
talking out of turn.
Brothers,
you know we can't
fight fire with fire.
We must oblige
to what our Lord asks.
Matthew 5:38-40.
"But I tell you,
"do not resist an evil person.
"If anyone slaps you
on the right cheek,
turn to them
the other cheek, also."
Look what the cat dragged in.
Oh, I've been meaning to
ask y'all something.
Claudette,
we need your help.
What's going on? I believe
my power has finally emerged.
Does this have anything to do
with what happened
with that guard at the hotel?
Yes, it does.
It won't take more than a minute
but will be immensely helpful.
Cut me.
Uh, me?
Oh, hell, give it here.
Not too deep.
Now what?
Oh, the discomfort.
Almost immediately
this time.
I feel better now.
Lord have mercy.
Miss Claudette,
thank you so very much.
Please, if there's anything
I can do for you...
You both can help me.
What I was gonna ask
any interest in a drink
on the house tomorrow night?
Okay, Jess, I know
I owe you an apology
for flaking the other night,
but I got called
into an emergency
- for the 4,400.
- I'm just sorry
you have to work so closely
with them.
I mean, they are dangerous.
Right?
You know,
a lot of them are real cool.
Nice folks.
I don't really know
that they're dangerous.
Are you serious?
Because I do.
I know firsthand,
up close and personal.
Well, when you throw
human beings in a cage
like they're animals,
they're gonna act like one.
Are they human?
I mean, 'cause their blood work
says otherwise.
- And, uh, oh, yeah, they - traveled through time.
- Wait, blood work?
You never mentioned anything
about that.
I barely see you.
Why would I?
- That's classified.
- Well, I think it's kind of important
for me to know what y'all
are planning on doing with them.
So, does this
blood work revelation
have anything to do
with these new extensive
contracts they have to sign
just to stay in the hotel?
So,
this is what this is?
Wow, Keisha.
You, uh, feed me, pump me
for information. Jess, no.
It's not how it seems.
I think it's exactly
how it seems.
I am
drowning, Keisha.
And I was
really hoping
that you could be the one person
that I could count on.
But you being a real,
actual, supportive partner?
I mean, who was I
kidding? I may not know
who you are anymore,
but at least you're consistent.
You're not gonna fight.
And you're not gonna fight
for me.
I'm done.
So, they all your kind?
You all right there, big guy?
Uh...
You're looking a little pale.
Like you could use some water.
Oh, but maybe not
this one, though,
with my dirty 4,400 fingers
all over the glass and all.
Yoo-hoo, can I get
some help over here?
Can I get a Moscow mule?
Make that two Moscow mules.
And a menu? Excuse me.
All right, hey, hey, that's it!
All you freaks
need to get the hell
out of here.
I have the right
to refuse service
to anyone.
Nope. That belongs to me.
And I have the right to
fire those who don't fit
the culture of my establishment,
which includes bigots.
So grab your crap and get out.
These freaks aren't even human.
And what do you know
about being human?
All I know is
there's a whole lot more
who see you all
the same way I do.
I would like to propose a toast.
To Miss Claudette and the feat
she so skillfully pulled off.
Here, here.
Yes. That was, like,
really empowering.
And thank you for ridding
this place of that gross,
hateful dude.
Seriously.
One less fearmonger
for us all to deal with.
If only he was the last one.
And to a fresh start.
The future is your oyster.
What may we expect next?
How about a promotion?
I'm short a bartender,
and word is,
- you're not as green - as you look.
- Really?
Yes. Absolutely.
Is this y'all's "to be
continued" about to continue?
'Cause there's definitely
a vibe happening here that...
that doesn't include me,
so I'm-a go...
elsewhere.
Thank you for your help.
I am unsure
what a future with this power
looks like, but...
I am certain if I have you
by my side,
then I will accept any fate.
Or...
am I foolish to hope for such?
I can't answer that, Andre,
until we figure some things out.
Thank you for being here.
Thank you for inviting me.
And seeing me as,
like, deep enough
to want to be a part of it.
This was the most important
I've ever felt.
Being a part of something
with purpose.
Yeah.
You all right?
Yeah, yeah.
Just figuring it all out,
you know?
I do.
You want to come over next
week for a girls' night?
I got to practice making all
these $20 two-sip concoctions
2021 folks are so willing
to pay for.
You know what? Yes.
A thousand percent yes.
Yes to you
and-and the girls' night
and dranks
and us having a purpose.
I'm gonna stay.
You sure you're okay?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- All right.
I'll dial you next week.
Okay, texting is more
what we do, but yes.
Hello?
Daddy?
You have no idea.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
Whiskey neat.
How'd you know?
I notice things.
Like how you trace the rim of
your glass when you're thinking.
Okay, uh,
I am not weird, I promise.
Look, I'm trying to say.
I-I notice things
because I'm-I'm interested.
In you.
Yeah, suffice to say,
I'm not girlfriend material.
Mine broke up with me
last night.
- You cheat?
- Nope.
I was just a cold bitch.
Not sure which is worse.
Mm. Cheater's always
gonna cheat.
A cold bitch just needs
something or someone
worth melting the ice for.
Look at you,
being our very own Tom Cruise
in Cocktail.
Tom who?
Only the biggest movie star
of our time.
Key word being "time."
Never mind.
I, um, I got you something.
What's this for?
Look, it's nothing fancy,
it's just...
a little something
for your first job
in 2021.
Uh, maybe
save opening it
for the end of the night.
- Can I pour you a drink?
- Sure.
- I'll be your guinea pig.
- Please.
I've been pouring men's drinks
for longer
than I care to remember.
Least now I'm getting paid
for it.
Thank you, for all this.
You're the one who did it,
Claudette.
You made all this happen.
Don't forget that.
Thank you for walking me back.
May I?
Shanice, I... Listen...
No... Truly, you...
Andre.
Talk.
I am deeply apologetic for not
telling you about Mariah.
I'm unsure what
I was thinking, or...
I was not using my faculties
at all.
All I know is I didn't want
to upset you.
Thank you.
That's all I wanted to hear.
An apology
with sincerity
and without a "but"
to negate it all.
Is this the reason you've been
acting strange around me?
Or does it have to
do with me saying.
Logan's name in my sleep?
I guess apologizing on behalf
of my subconscious mind
doesn't make sense.
I am sorry, though,
that you had to hear.
Truly.
An apology is unnecessary,
because I don't care.
You don't care?
Why, not at all.
Then what are we doing?
Because I care, Andre.
Of course I care,
I just don't care care,
because not caring is not what
I intended to communicate.
English, please.
I am speaking English.
Not jibber-jabber.
You know what I mean.
I don't know how to speak
like you.
I don't know
how to act like you,
I don't know how to be
with you, here,
in this time,
where men and women
love multiple people
simultaneously
and ex-lovers are friends,
and while that is
lovely and wonderful,
it's also supposed
to be so normal,
because today everything
is so nonchalant.
I'm trying to be just
as laissez-faire
so I don't scare
you away, but...
perhaps I don't belong in 2021.
Because I don't
want to share you,
not even in your
subconscious mind.
Because I care.
You do care.
And I do, too.
Lord have mercy, you scared me.
I am so sorry, I didn't
mean to scare you at all.
I just, no, I came because
I didn't want you to be alone.
Not like that.
I mean, with everything
that went down tonight,
and... with Barney.
And I know you're all
independent and everything,
now that...
Oh. Okay.
Oh. Sorry.
Oh, w-w-wait. Watch this.
I know, right?
Smart and romantic.
And how much
have you had to drink?
Oh, not enough to not consent.
Because I consent.
Do you?
Okay. Uh...
I don't do the rebound thing.
This needs to be real
if you want more.
Or we can...
talk about it tomorrow.
LaDonna?
She's gone?
"Push here."
Hey, so I know how scary
computers are to you and that
you can barely even send a text.
Well, actually, you cannot,
because one time we tried that,
and you sent a bunch
of commas to yourself.
So, anyways, um, because
you are a hundred years old,
I'm going to speak
very slow and clearly
about how to get
the files from Ypsi Med.
And I know you might
be feeling anxious
and want to eat your feelings,
so I did leave you
my favorite snack.
You're welcome.
Um, but seriously, Andre,
if at any time
this feels, like,
too beep-boop-boppy for you,
reach out to Soraya.
She's on our side. Okay, bye.
I'm just kidding. Um...
I mean, this is goodbye.
Um, and I'm...
I'm sorry it sucks, but...
this would've been way too hard
to do in person, so...
Uh, but at least
I will have these.
That's a good one.
Hey.
So, what'd you figure out?
Okay, this "contract" is a trap.
It's not so much a contract
as it is laying the groundwork
for the government to put people
under conservatorship.
Wait, what? But
that robs the 4,400
of their rights, financial
decision-making...
- Their freedom.
- And it's all legal.
But why would Rev encourage
so many people
to sign a document
that's gonna be so restrictive?
Brothers and sisters,
before we begin,
I'd like to thank you
for a smooth last couple days.
Brother Bill Greene and I
rely on your trust
as we do everything... Yeah, the
most important question right now
is how many of them
have signed this?
What's wrong?
Did something happen
to one of our members?
They're fine.
Everyone's fine.
Who I'm worried about is you.
Heavens, why? I'm good.
I don't know if that is true,
given your recent outbursts.
I find them
rather alarming, dear.
I don't understand. I-I haven't
done nothing but offer you
and our members
something different to try.
There are places that specialize
in helping women like yourself...
Women with divergent
thinking... get back on track.
Jimmy, I-I don't need
no help thinking. I...
It will only be a few months.
Months? Where in Lord's name...
Provided you be a good woman,
shouldn't take too long
to get you right as rain.
Jimmy, I-I don't need
none of that.
I'm sorry
for what I said. I-I...
For speaking out of turn.
It was a mistake.
I-I'll do whatever
you tell me to do.
I-I promise I won't say
nothing anymore.
I won't say a word.
I-I won't say a word.
Jimmy, please don't this to me.
But you made me do it, dear.
Jimmy.
Jimmy, please.
- Let's go.
- Yes, sir.
Open the door, Claudette.
Claudette, open this door.
Captioning sponsored by CBS.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org