Lord, I always put
my trust in you.
I made a big leap of faith,
and I thought it was
the right thing.
But I find myself 30 years
in the future and...
I've experienced
the impossible.
Why are the taking
the BestTime snacks?
They took the piano, too.
They're punishing us.
For Shanice escaping.
We've got
to get out of here.
I asked you for a sign.
This must be the sign,
but... help me understand.
What am I to do?
Hey.
They need to talk to you.
You want to tell us
how you escaped
from the hotel the other day?
Do you want to tell me
when you plan on
letting us out of here for good?
Since as far as I can tell,
you have
no lawful grounds to detain us.
You took a huge risk.
Potentially exposing
your husband and daughter...
To what? They're my family.
Look, Shanice,
you know we're not the enemy.
Michigan Penal Code,
Article 328.
"A person who commits
unlawful imprisonment
is guilty of a felony."
Just tell us
who you were working with.
Are they the same ones
who leaked to the public
that you all
are missing persons?
That there are 4,400 of you?
"Punishable...
"by not more than 15 years
or a fine of not more
than $20,000, or both."
So have you all figured out
how we apparently
travelled through time?
We don't know that's
what happened.
So how come the last thing
I remember
it was 2015...
and now it's 2021?
Maybe you were taken somewhere?
Maybe someone doesn't
want you to remember? Ew, who?
Well, that's what we want to
find out, but most importantly,
we want to make sure
that everybody's okay now.
Okay, well, we'd be more okay
if we could get out of here.
And if we didn't have to wear
these truly hideous
synthetic fabrics.
Like, can you do something
about this...
travesty?
I don't know anything
about how Shanice got out.
Really? Because
she was last seen
headed to the bathroom with you.
Yo.
She's just a kid. And kids lie, too.
Okay, you really
think interrogating minors is
is the best way to figure...
Well, I think we were just
about done here anyway.
Hey, come on, I'll have one
of the guards take you back.
Why did you say what you
said the other night?
You said to tell Jharrel that...
Manny's all right, that
he's sorry for everything.
How do you know
Jharrel's brother?
I don't know him.
Then why were you talking
about him?
Does it have something to do
with why you all are here?
No. I-I-I guess it was
just something I heard.
From who? From Jharrel?
No. Just...
people talk.
So it was what... a prank?
Is this whole thing
some kind of prank?
We are trying to help you all.
You need to be honest with
us, not jerk us around...
Look, I can't eat the new food.
And they took away
the BestTime Bars.
I love the BestTime Bars.
I've cooperated
since we've got here.
But there has been
no movement to get us out.
It would help if people
weren't leaking information
to the press
and escaping custody.
Those sound like your problems.
Not mine.
And what is your
problem, Reverend?
I lost something that night.
On Belle Isle.
And I need to get it to someone.
A woman and a child.
No one is going anywhere.
Certainly not back to the
scene of what happened.
And families aren't being
notified until we know more.
How about this?
You give me their names,
and I'll see if I can locate
this woman and child.
And in return...
you tell me everything you know
about how you got here.
And Belle Isle?
We'll see.
First, Shanice Murray.
She escaped.
I think she knows more
than she's letting on.
Well...
everyone has secrets.
Sure you can't stay any longer?
I'm on the swing shift later.
I'd love to.
But I've got to get back.
My father has me
leading the service today.
Guess you haven't told them yet?
I...
I'm just waiting
for the right moment.
I want to make sure
they really understand.
Understand why their precious,
perfect baby boy
would end up
with someone like me?
Darlene... it's not like that.
I'm going on 17 weeks now.
You said you wanted to keep it.
That you wanted us
to do this together. I do!
Because I can't afford
a baby on my own.
You're not on your own.
I'm with you.
I thank the Lord every day.
He brought you to me, Darlene.
But they've got their
old ways of thinking.
I've got to show them
that they're wrong.
You trust me, right?
Yeah.
Yeah? Yeah...
Do you really think
intimidation tactics
like those interrogations
are gonna work?
We have to use
every tactic we can.
Keisha, they are scared.
Shanice Murray escaped.
Yes, because they're being
locked up here for no reason.
Well, I want to know
who she's working with.
Where's this
I.T. guy anyway?
Present!
And she wasn't
working with anyone.
That's what I wanted
to show you.
Uh, Keisha and Jharrel, right?
Cool to meet you.
I'm Soraya. Texpert.
You like that?
I'm making it a thing.
They hired me to shore up
the security in this place,
which is, yeah, lacking.
But look.
Here's the footage from the
cameras where Shanice escaped.
Okay, we've seen this footage.
Seems like the doors just...
opened.
Then someone moved
the cameras remotely,
so we can't see
how she opened the door.
No. Her body language says that
she wasn't prepared for this.
Wasn't planning on escaping.
She took advantage
of a door opening.
Are you a body language
expert, too?
Oh, I watch a lot
of reality television.
People say it's trash, but...
I say it's a masterclass
on human nature.
So we're listening
to a specialist
that trained
in the Ex-Wivesfranchise?
Uh... technically I went
to M.I.T. and Quantico, too.
But that was a lot more boring.
What's not boring is this gig.
Had to get clearance
to take it, but...
I had no idea
it would be... this.
Yeah, and what is this?
Because I can't get
anything real out of them.
Well, it's clear they have
no idea what happened to them.
Which is consistent with
reportings of alien encounters.
Aliens? Seriously?
Maybe? But the
simplest explanation
is that they time travelled,
clearly against their will.
So... who did that to them?
I'm sorry, time travel is
the simplest explanation?
Except time travel isn't
a thing.
Mm. So what's the
logical explanation?
Well, it is illogical to think
that we have all the tools
or the means to explain
everything in the universe.
So...
why didn't we let Shanice Murray
have a minute to catch up
with her family after she
was cleared by medical?
That is a great question.
Good point...
about the family.
We cleared the husband
after her visit, but...
maybe he can get something
out of her that I can't.
Maybe she'll tell him
what she knows.
Yo, what's her deal?
Is she single?
I'm just here to talk.
We, uh...
we saw on the news.
Is that what
Shanice is a part of?
That 4,400 people?
So you didn't have
anything to do
with leaking it to the press?
Leak what?
I don't know anything.
Shanice just shows up
at my doorstep after being gone
16 years,
talking like she just left.
The government is...
trying to figure it out.
Okay, we're trying to help.
Is, uh...
is she okay?
She's... angry.
Reciting the Michigan Penal Code
nonstop.
Yeah, it sounds like Shanice.
Listen, I'll admit
that I can't get through to her.
I want to try to figure out
what's going on.
I want to help her.
She won't talk to me.
But maybe she'll talk to you.
No. No, no, no.
No, listen,
we can't be involved.
You know, I have a daughter
I have to think about.
And that's a big part
of the reason I'm here.
I don't think you
or your family has anything
to do with this, but it would
go a long way in easing
everyone's mind if you help.
Uh-uh, I'm not doing it.
I already lost a nail in here
and it's probably from cutting
your arm open over and over
again... Doc, tell her.
This does not seem wise.
I swore an oath
to first do no harm.
And that is Doc talk
for "it's cray."
Don't you want to know
the limits of this thing?
What exactly I can take?
Lord have mercy...
Just break my finger!
We already know I
can heal from cuts.
If I can heal from anything...
I can isolate one of them guards
and take 'em on.
And then if they beat me
or shoot me...
whatever... I can withstand it
and escape and figure out
how to get everyone out.
Well...
experimentation and observation
are the best road
to discovery.
Yes.
Y'all are really kind
of demented, you know that?
Never mind, Doc,
Ladonna here just...
just doesn't have
the stomach for it.
Now I didn't take her
for a fraidy cat...
Whoa, I'm not afraid
of anything, okay?
You're just-just too weak
to get the job done, dear...
It's fine.
Excuse me?
Look, I once took out
a backstabbing skank
with one four-inch stiletto
to the chin, so I am not weak.
I didn't quite follow all that...
Pray tell, what is a skank?
Prove it.
Oh! Miss Ladonna!
She made me.
Fascinating.
It worked! Oh, my God.
Hmm? GUARD: Count! Count!
Line 'em up! GUARD 2: All right,
let's line up!
Okay, everybody, listen up!
Moving forward,
we'll be doing counts.
This group is assigned to this
checkpoint. When you hear
the alarm, you have
two minutes to get here.
You're being fitted
with GPS ankle bands.
Just in case anyone gets any
bright ideas about sneaking out.
Again.
These measures are in place for
you and everyone else's safety.
Do we understand each other?
Do you think this is funny?
N-No.Then shut your mouth.
Oh, we know about you already.
Got something to say?
Why am I back here?
Why won't you guys tell me
what's going on?
Logan?
Hi, Shanice.
So, uh...
this is where you've been.
Well, just for
the last few days.
Be... fore that I was home
and then... Right, you, uh...
you somehow don't remember what
happened for the past 16 years.
Do I look
like I've aged 16 years?
You know, this place reminds me
of that hotel we stayed at.
Up north.Yeah.
When we had to have
the house fumigated.
Still can't believe you
shelled out for that trip.
You were
six months pregnant, Shanice.
What, I'm gonna make you sleep
on Mrs. Grover's
guest bed?
It's like sleeping
on a slab of concrete.
Why did you come?
You really don't know
what happened?
I only know that I didn't leave.
Yes, I thought about
leaving at one point.
It was postpartum depression.
It was bad and I had
some... dark nights.
You wrote me
a goodbye note, Shanice.
I mean, I-I knew
it was hard, but I...
You never told me.
I didn't know how.
How was I supposed
to tell you that?
I would've helped, I would've.
But you were never good
at asking for help.
Yeah, well, can I...?
Will you bring Mariah?
I'd like to...
I guess, meet her.
Get to know her.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
Not yet, at least.
I mean, you said for yourself
you don't know what's happening.
And the government
seems to think that
you're involved in... I'm not!
That is so ridiculous.
I just don't think I want
to expose her to
it all just yet.
I mean, what if you...?
What if you disappear again?
I should go.
Do you and, um...?
Do you have any other children?
No.
I'm glad you're okay
and I'm just...
I'm sorry.
Okay, folks!
Now this is what we like to see.
Everybody follows the rules.
Everything will be peachy.
Just like I said.
See you at the next one.
Hey.
I heard you talking about trying
to get us back to Belle Isle.
It's an idea
I've been pondering.
Do you think it might
reverse everything, like,
somehow take us back to before?
Maybe it's like
that new show Outlander.
This chick finds some kind
of altar in the woods,
and then all of a sudden,
she's at this castle
with this hottie in a kilt
and they go... at it.
Wow.
I'm just saying homegirl had
to go back and frolic
at the Druid Stones to time travel,
so...
What are you three
always off talking about?
You know, mostly fashion.
And, um...
old-timey doctor...
stuff.
I got to go.
What was that?
What was... what?
Was that a BestTime bar?
So you decided to make
this Belle Isle trip
a whole campaign?
I'm determined and somehow
I didn't think
you were gonna make it happen.
You're selling these people
a bill of goods.
You've got them thinking that if
they go there, this whole thing
will be undone and they'll just
go back to living their lives.
Do you know that to be false?
Can you explain what's happened?
You just want to go back
for whatever you left there.
You'll get that.
And what do they get... nothing.
They'll get out.
Even if it's for a short time.
We've been trapped
like rats in a cage.
It'll be something.
They think
this will take them back.
That whatever happened
will happen again.
How do you think they'll feel
when it doesn't?
How do you know it won't?
You're lying to them.
Who knows?
Maybe it will happen again
and we'll all be gone.
But I need to make things right
with my family either way.
I have to.
And may we hold His holiness
close to our hearts!
Amen, and may we live
in the light
that shines in each
and every one of us!
Praise God in Jesus' name!
Somebody show Him the love
that He deserves!
Somebody show Him
the praise that He deserves!
Glory be to God!
Glory be to God.
Yes, praise Him!
Hallelujah!
The Lord flowed
through you today, son.
Thank you, sir.
I felt His presence.
It felt good out there.
You're a natural.
It's why your mother
and I are so pleased
you're here to help
us guide the flock.
And we've been talking.
It's about time to give you
some more responsibility.
And time for you to start
thinking about your future.
I have been thinking
about my future.
And I've actually been
meaning to tell you.
There's a woman
I've been seeing.
A woman?
Who's her family?
She's not...
she's not a part of the faith.
But I love her
and I think if you just...
Son...
you're young.
And you want to sow
some wild oats.
And that's all right.
The Lord understands
your need for comfort.
But...
all this will be yours someday.
You're gonna need
to find someone
who can share
this burden with you,
who understands your needs
and the life you must lead.
But I don't need
all of this to serve the Lord.
These people, they're pouring
out their money.
That ring on your finger
is worth more than most
of them make in a year.
It doesn't feel right.
It's not only right.
It's ordained.
This ring reminds me
of who I am.
This is how we praise Him.
This is all
in Jesus' name.
Yes, sir.
All right.
Amen.Amen.
Hey, sweetheart.
I thought you were, uh...
going over to Naima's to study?
Dad, why did you go see her
without telling me?
How did you...?
I knew I shouldn't have let you
download that door camera app.
Please, you can't even
figure out how it works.
You can't go eavesdropping
on people's conversations
like that, okay?
Some kids at school were talking
about the Belle Isle people.
Saying it might be some
foreign invasion
or something,
but she's one of them so...
We don't know anything
about her situation.
I thought you'd talk to me
about it.
You usually, like,
talk to me about stuff.
I know.
I'm know, I'm sorry, but...
look, this is...
you know, it's complicated,
and I just don't want it
to interfere with your life.
But I want to see her, too.
I mean, I've never...
I only have pictures of her.
You know?
And I want to know
what happened.
She doesn't even know.
And until we have
more information,
it's just not safe to see her.
But, Dad... Mariah... I mean it.
This conversation is
closed for now.
So I found this room
when I was poking around.
Before, the snacks were
just out, but I guess
they locked 'em up.
So let's just go, okay?
That guard takes
a long break,
but he'll be back soon.
What's going on?
I don't
even really totally
know that I can do it.
Yes, you do.
Seriously, what's going on?
Oh, my...
Wait a minute.
Did you...?
Did you just...?
Wait, can you...?
What?!
Hayden.
So, like, we're all clear
that you just did that
with your mind, right?
Are you, like, a superhero
or something?
I don't know.
I've only been able to do it
since... you know.
Can I do that?
I don't, I don't
think I can do that.
Yeah, me, neither.
Dude. Aren't these sick?
Mmm, yummy, snacks. BestTime Bars are
I'm starving. So much fun...
Hey, wait a minute, you guys
are not supposed to be in here.
You're gonna be
in so much trouble!
You better put that stuff back
right now!
How did you even get in here? Keep singing!
What? Just do it!
Okay, uh, Best...
I love chips.
I think as long
as you sing about snacks,
the guard... wants snacks?
BestTime Bars are number one.
It doesn't seem
to affect us, though.
Just him.
That is tubular. Make it a BestTime Bar.
Mrs. Murray?
Well...
you have that wide-eyed air
about you.
New to the sleepless club?
Yeah, I guess I am.
I always slept like the dead.
But here...
after everything...
Yes, one's troubles
can have a way
of invading one's mind
and chasing off rest
in even the most weary.
My husband came to see me today.
And when I first
saw him,
I thought it was a good thing.
An amazing thing.
You know, like maybe
we could fix this?
But the gulf between us now
feels so wide.
I don't know that
I'll ever get my family back.
It will take time.
A strange
and fickle beast, apparently.
You must have people
that you miss,
that you want to connect with?
It's 2021.
Everyone is dead.
The reverend wants
to go back to Belle Isle.
Thinks it might
help us figure something out.
It certainly seems
a worthy experiment.
What do you think
would occur there?
I don't know.
It seems crazy to think...
But the crazy thing happened.
And maybe if we go back
to Belle Isle,
it'll all...
reverse itself.
Maybe we can all get everything
and everyone... back.
And maybe I can...
get my family back.
Six...
382, four... KEN: Seven...
79... Watch it!
Nine...
Ten, 11...
12, 13...
14, 15,
16, 17, 18...
I don't know
why I ever believed you.
You're never gonna
go against them.
leave this place
because you like it too much.
Of course I like it...
I'm a man of God.
He's everything to me.
No, it's not that.
It's your family.
It's the money and the power.
It's how you can
manipulate people.
How you can make them believe
you, do whatever you want.
That's not true.
What we have is real.
I'm gonna make it right.
I will!
They'll listen to reason.
They'll see our love
and they'll understand.
No, they won't.
You're gonna have
to make a choice.
And I don't think
you're gonna choose me.
Or our child.
You're gonna turn out
just like him.
Okay, that's enough.
That was uncalled for!
Why in the world would you
attack him?!
He didn't do anything!
I started it! Kid's a troublemaker.
Don't like his attitude.
Let me examine him
and make sure nothing is broken.
Everybody needs to understand
that order will be maintained!
You don't make the rules here!
We do.
He's fine. Stay where you are.
Come on.
You all right?
Sure.
Just trying to recover
from getting attacked
by that power-tripping guard.
I was finally starting to feel
a little better, like maybe
there's a reason for all of
this, especially after I learned
I could just sing and...
You-you could what?
You could sing and...
Never mind.
But what about going
to Belle Isle?
Maybe the green lights
will come and take us back?
Maybe we can finally
get out of here for good?
Listen, I know I said that
we should go there,
but I'm not sure it would
actually work that way.
Okay.
I just...
I thought you knew
how to make things better.
It just feels like nobody cares.
Like, nobody's trying
to help us.
Going back to Belle Isle
just felt like...
I don't know.
Hope?
She's not the wife you
would've chosen,
but she's my choice.
Don't you think you're going
to bring that woman
into this place.
She's the woman I love.
And what about your
responsibilities here?
What about your responsibility
to our people?
You call it responsibility, but
who really benefits?
Darlene's right.
What we do here is hypocrisy.
We built this house
on God's Word.
We built this congregation
at His command.
Maybe.
But now we use it for us.
If that's what you see,
then you are lost in your faith.
Every day we preach the Word
to those people out there,
because they are tired,
they are sad, anxious,
in pain,
because the world is hard.
I know that... You don't know!
You don't know
or you wouldn't be standing here
giving me this nonsense.
The Lord asked us, this family,
to sacrifice.
To dedicate our lives to others.
They need to see that the
Lord put us here for them.
They need to see
that we can bear their burdens
and that there are
rewards beyond the material.
Because what people need...
What the Lord knows they need...
Is hope.
And if you don't know
that that's worth more
than dollars and cents...
then you really
don't understand, son.
Who do you think you are?
That you can reject God's plan?
It was stupid.
It's not stupid.
It's what everyone needs.
I see that now.
It's my calling.
I haven't been listening.
Listening to who? You
have my promise, Noah.
I'm going to make things right.
But first I need to know
everything that's going on.
I feel like there's things
that I don't know about.
Like with the singing.
Will you share with me?
Hey there.
I heard there was an incident
with one of the guards?
Wanted to check on you.
And...
uh, bring you some food.
Made it myself.
Since...
uh, you said
you didn't like the food.
What about my friend?
The guards are here
for your protection.
When any of you disobeys
the rules, it...
makes things unsafe
for everyone.
We're not safe now.
How can we be when
we're not free?!
Hey.
Yo.
So...
why did you want me
to meet you here?
Wanted to talk somewhere
without cameras tracking
our every move.
I think we should take people
back to Belle Isle.
Okay...
I-I've heard rumblings
among the 4,400 about this,
but youwant to do this?
Some of these people seem
to be doing badly here.
If we can show them that
we're trying to help them...
Mm-hmm, and who knows,
maybe they're right,
and Belle Isle is some kind
of time machine.Funny.
I will be watching every minute,
see if we can get some clues,
some idea of... what happened
last time they were there.
And I am going to enjoy
seeing these people
actually get some fresh air.
Whatever happens,
they deserve that.
So... you gonna sweet-talk
your girl into it?
I will handle Agent Tanner.
She got called
to oversee an emergency
at the Ypsi Med facility.
Took a bunch of the guards
with her,
so the place is as unguarded
as it will ever be.
Okay, night trip to Belle Isle
it is, but you and me
can't take everybody.
Maybe we can slip a group out
after their count.
Mm, and they're all wearing
ankle monitors,
so we'll be able find them
if anything goes wrong.
But... I have my body-worn
camera just in case.
Yes, yes,
everyone will be tracked
and monitored
within an inch of their life.
A police state in action. Hey.
We stay vigilant.
Okay?
Me and my brother used to
draw these everywhere.
It was a game to play.
One of us would start out a
clock, the other one would add
another number and we'd...
keep adding numbers
until it was done.
Think he might still be here?
I don't know, these people
arriving here, they...
brought back my hope
for finding him.
So if...
somehow this whole thing
works out...
and they do go back, then...
I don't know, maybe I can put
this whole thing behind me.
Finally let go of Manny, too.
To Belle Isle.
Hey.
I heard you earlier.
I-I hope this helps you
feel better.
That you'll be out,
free for a bit.
Oh, I'm not going.
I have to stay here.
But why? I-I thought... Are you sure?
I just have to stay... here.
See you when we get back?
Yeah.
So...
you notice anything suspicious?
I mean, have you figured
out the mystery yet?
Guess the time machine's
not working tonight.
That's what you wanted
to come back here for?
Originally, yes.
Nice rock.
Worth a pretty penny.
It is. I was gonna
give it to Darlene
to show her that I had always
intended to do right by her.
I tracked her down,
her and her son.
Your son?
A son?
I have a son?
I have to let them go.
But why...
It's not what the
Lord wanted for me.
I made the wrong choice then.
And I think
that's why this is happening.
He is showing me
the way... that I must
accept my calling.
What calling?
To be here.
To be present. To believe.
Mark 9:23...
"All things are possible
to him that believeth."
If you'll excuse me, I'd...
like to lead a prayer.
First, let's take a moment
to give thanks for being here.
Lord, the fresh air feels good.
It's strange being back
in this place, isn't it?
What we've gone through
is a lot for any human to bear,
and they try
to take our humanity away,
but they won't succeed.
We were taken away from the comfort
of our lives, And if that mocking
taken from those we love, Bird don't sing
taken from Mama's gonna
our realities as we knew
it! Buy you a diamond ring.
And... And if
some of you came here
tonight That diamond ring
hoping to make that all
go away. Turns brass
I'm here to tell you Mama's gonna buy you
it won't. A looking glass.
We must accept the truth
of our tribulations.
We must accept the seriousness
of our circumstance,
because the truth is,
we were brought
forward in time, yes?
But the Lord didn't
bring us here.
To flounder alone.
He gave us each other.
And he gave us gifts.
Let's give praise
to Sister Mildred.
She's making this happen
with her mind.
And Brother Noah is
using his voice
to give us the privacy
of this moment.
Just us...
without our keepers.
They're fine, just in slumber.
Because I needed
this moment to reach you,
to let you all know
that you're special.
To let you all know
that we've been taken
and brought here for a reason.
We have been brought here
on a mission!
We don't know
exactly what it is yet.
But I believe
that I am here to lead you.
Look within yourself.
See yourself
and know your worth.
Know your power
and own your gifts.
Because who are we
to question God's plan?
Extraordinary.
I assumed there were others,
but I never imagined
this.
I just thought finally
maybe it was my turn
to be the one people turn to.
But him.
Give him another two weeks,
and they'll be
eating out
of the palm of his hand.
And I do not trust
what he will do
with that kind of power.
Well... they didn't
get taken back.
Instead we all just,
what, fell asleep?
Something put us to sleep.
Something put everybody
on Belle Isle
to sleep at the same time.
The question is: What?
The 4,400 seemed
just as confused
as we were
when all of us woke up.
No, we don't know
what happened to them.
We were asleep.
Okay, well, we know
that they all got on the bus
with us just as planned.
Everyone accounted for.
No trouble at all.
What, you think
they were faking it?
I think I'm gonna find out.
Pulling up the footage
from my body cam right now.
Score one for our police state,
by the way.
Ah, cop's got jokes.
At least we can
actually see what...
happened.
So, I took
the ankle bracelets off-line
for a little unscheduled
reboot, like you asked.
But I'm dying
to know what happened.
Was it like an Outlander
kind of situation
or, like, more
like Close Encounters?
I'm still not sure
why you're even helping us.
I don't like this whole
operation.
From what I can tell,
these people shouldn't be
locked up.
And even if they are
aliens or clones
or run-of-the-mill
time travelers,
those things aren't even crimes.
So if you two are
trying to help them,
I'll help you.
Oh, come on.
We should show her.
Damn it, the camera broke.
Like, what happened?
Was there some kind
of sonic weapon
that put everyone to sleep?
Or is it the atmosphere
on Belle Isle?
I don't know.
But I want to find out.
Let me go back to the office,
and see if I can pull
anything else from the footage.
You coming?
I can't.
Got to go lie to my girlfriend.
I'll send you the file.
Girlfriend?
Care for a drink?
No thanks.
I'm waiting for my lady.
That for her?
In a way.
This is the key
to our future together.
Worth a fortune.
I'll be able to give her
everything she needs,
everything she deserves
with this.
It's the start
of our life together.
That looks heavy.
I think something like that
might weigh me down.
Me, too.
It would tempt me into becoming
someone I didn't want to be.
And that's
why I'm never gonna wear it.
I'm gonna be free.
We're gonna be free.
If she comes looking for me,
can you tell her
I'll be right back?
Sure thing.
Thank you.
Excu...? He just
went to the restroom.
But he'll be right back.
Great. I'll wait.
That ended up being
a rather eventful evening.
I guess I kind of got
wrapped up in the idea
that it was gonna be
more eventful.
That we'd return.
I, too, am sad for what we lost.
But what we've all gone through,
it's truly awe-inspiring and...
I'm also grateful
for what I have found here.
Me, too, Doc.
So...
uh, I think we continue to be
in a confounding situation.
As to what that heralds
for our future,
I...
cannot say.
Perhaps it will become
clearer in the morning.
Perhaps.
Good night.
Hi, Mom.
All right, I'll be
right back, Soraya.