All right, listen up.
Here's a map of the area.
Our 44orum brethren are
setting up a perimeter
outside the hotel as we speak.
May even send some guys in
to scope the inside.
We'll make sure
those mutants stay put
until they get
what's coming to them.
Then we'll flush 'em back
to the freak show
where they belong.
You good, Shane?
You've been mighty quiet
this whole time.
Not afraid to go toe-to-toe
with these creatures, are you?
Damn!
It's always the quiet ones.
It's game time, boys!
Let's make 'em pay!
Run 'em out of town. Yeah!
Let's clean up the
Motor City! Yeah.
Okay, you can come out.
Look, it's safer down here
than in one of those rooms.
Seriously, Manny,
it's safe down here.
Only a handful of people
know about this place, and...
we can trust them.
Don't think I'm ever
gonna get used to that.
Man.
I can't believe you're
back here in the flesh.
Well, kind of.
Was starting to think
I'd never see you again.
I would never let that happen.
So...
tell me everything.
What happened to you?
I arrived at Belle Isle
just like the other 4,400,
confused and terrified.
Then I discovered that
I could make myself invisible,
which freaked me out at first.
Then...
I realized that I could hide
from the government.
When they did their counts,
I stayed off their radar.
Damn.
But why didn't you tell me
you were here?
I mean, why the-the clocks,
the cyphers? I...
You were a part-time Fed, Jha.
I needed to make sure
that I could trust you,
that you knew me enough
to find me.
What the hell, Manny?
I mean, your tests
almost drove me insane.
Government's been after me
since before I got taken.
Now that I'm back, they
definitely see me as a threat.
And trust me,
they're not gonna do anything
to protect the folks
in this sanctuary
from the actual threat
that's coming.
There's this 44orum online,
people spreading hate
and misinformation.
Yeah, I read about
those asshats.
You think they're actually
planning something?
Yes, I do.
And with the government
rounding us up
from the tip line,
we got to convince any 4,400
that's still out there
to come back here, ASAP.
We're stronger
if we're all here together.
Okay, but...
but what about you, huh?
How are you?
You okay?
Look, I'm worried
about all of y'all,
but... you,
you good?
I'm good.
I just want to make sure
we're all safe.
We don't know much about them,
but things seem promising.
This BHN company is sending
food and other supplies.
They're letting us handle the
day-to-day running of the hotel.
Maybe they're legit.
Well, from what I found
from some Internet sleuthing,
Sienna Stone is
the founder and CEO.
She's some renegade,
anti-government
tech entrepreneur dedicated
to building sustainable
communities.
So maybe their heart's
in the right place,
unlike the government.
Reverend Johnston.
Ji-Eun.
You're all right.
Yes, I am.
I thought you'd take your
chances anywhere else but here.
I'm sorry about that.
I just got freaked out.
I'm just glad I was there
to rescue her
from that jerk that called her
into the tip line.
So, you and your friend
would like to seek sanctuary?
Not exactly.
I heard a rumor you could
take away powers.
Well, I...
Sometimes, I glow
without even knowing it.
Harold and I want to live
a normal life
together.
I want you to take
my powers away,
and I want you to marry us.
We know what it looks like.
Ji-Eun and I were together
when she went missing,
but I never gave up hope.
I knew one day I'd find her.
And here we are
over 30 years later.
Time couldn't stop our love.
Your story is proof
that God looks out
for true love and hope.
I would be honored
to officiate your wedding
and relieve you of your powers
if you're sure.
Yes, I am. Thank you.
There's so much to do.
I don't
even know where to start.
Could you help me
with everything?
Since you've been married
before?
Mr. Davis.
There's someone here
that say they know you.
I think there's been
a misunderstanding.
I've never seen this man before.
Oh, my word!
Gotcha. Sherlock.
Watson.
Ah, I'm so pleased it's you
and not one of those people.
Have you heard of this 44orum?
The patriotic nuts
who believe things about us
that break my brain?
Yeah. Indeed.
There are rumors that
some of them are posing
as 4,400 seeking sanctuary
in order to infiltrate
the hotel,
which is why we have
guard shifts
to provide security now.
It's not a rumor. It's true.
We have to be careful in here.
Okay? They are coming for us.
How do you know this?
Are you...
all right?
Yeah. Yeah. Just...
glad to be back.
I'm so pleased to see you.
She's a real beauty.
Bought it from an estate sale
a few months ago.
But I can't seem to get my hands
on the original track
from the 1930s.
I could go with you next time.
We could find our next project.
Like that time we restored
that phonograph from the 1880s.
Yeah.
It's good to have my trusty
assistant back in the attic.
And up next,
the radio host you hate to love,
Kevin Wellington,
telling it like it is.
Giving you
the kick in the butt you need
to stop being one of the sheep
and start thinking for yourself.
You're listening
to that man again?
You've been playing him nonstop
since I got back.
What happened to
Miami's News Breakdown?
What do you know about
Kevin Wellington?
Nothing.
Except he's clearly
a racist radio hack
who's making America dumber
by the second.
All he does is
spin outrageous stories
about everyone from-from
immigrants to Black people
to the 4,400.
And right now,
I'm kind of all three.
Yeah, well, he keeps it real.
He makes some good points, too.
Oh, my God, I totally forgot.
The, uh, the Meet the 4,400
event is on.
You can see my friends.
Yeah, um, you know,
having Hayden in our home
was unexpected,
but, you know, he's brought
so much good into our lives.
I can't imagine him being anywhere else.
Okay, so that's Logan.
He's Shanice's, like, husband,
or ex or whatever.
All this stuff is just for show.
It's all fake. Daddy, it's not.
Just-just watch.
Oh, my God.
Up. Up in the window.
Up. Mildred?
That little white girl...
- Well, I'll give you a reason!
- She-She's doing this.
Oh, my God.
She's trying to murder that man.
No, no. She...
No, this is who they are.
This is what they can do.
No, no.
This is what you are.
Something's wrong.
I got to call Andre.
Thanks.
What are you doing?
Can I have my phone?
Dad?
Daddy?
Daddy, let me out!
Okay, well,
you know I had to ask.
At least see
if Mildred's interested.
I mean, she is kind of wanted
by...
well, everyone.
All right, cool. Thanks.
And Claudette is...
Big shocker... a no.
Claudette, huh?
Thought you and Carla were
going to make it.
Let's just say I wasn't
exactly the best partner
after you disappeared.
I mean,
she did everything she could
to help, but I was...
an undeserving ass.
I'm sorry, Jha. I...
I'm sorry it was
so hard for you.
No.
Just the man I was looking for.
Um, hey, what's up?
Can you get a marriage license
for Ji-Eun and Harold?
Since it's easier
for you to come and go.
Yeah, sure. This is my...
I'm Jorge.
Jharrel and I went
to college together.
Don't worry,
I'm a 4,400 supporter.
Reverend Johnston.
Pleasure to meet you. Likewise.
I should go.
Jharrel, thanks for your help.
No problem.
So,
we are Jorge now?
I can't let word get back
to the government.
I'll find you later.
You okay?
My powers, I... Um...
I can't turn invisible.
Wait, w-what do you mean?
I mean, I can't, like...
I've never not been able...
I mean, since it started,
I've never not been able to...
It's okay.
All right, just hide out here
until it comes back.
Then dive into this.
Always calmed you down,
remember?
I will help you figure this out
when I get back.
Andre said you were back.
How long are you visiting?
I'm staying.
I heard you're in charge
of room assignments.
Feels like I am
in charge of everything
around here.
Oh, I am a diplomat.
Events coordinator, landlord.
You name it.
But how are you?
Where have you been?
I'm fine. Fine.
I just could really use
a shower.
So I was hoping I could get
my old room back.
Or, honestly, any room.
It does not matter.
A lot of 4,400 are coming back,
so you may end up
with a roommate.
That's fine.
Be nice to not be alone for a change.
Great.
That makes my job easier.
And what is with this wedding
y'all are throwing
for Ji-Eun and her boo?
Because when I left,
we barely had money
for decent clothes,
and now there are
racks of dresses
for her to try on.
How can we afford all this?
Oh, when BHN found out
about the wedding,
they gave us money
to pay for it.
Sweet.
Or shady?
I don't know yet.
Hmm. Well, if you need a DJ,
I'm your girl.
I might just take you up
on that.
Great.
I love weddings.
You know, I always thought
my dad was gonna walk me
down the aisle, but...
things are kind of different
now.
It's clear that the 4,400
have been hiding
their true nature
from the world.
What could they want from...
Look, you have to stop this.
You have to let me go.
I'm just waiting for
the iguana to show itself.
What iguana?
I am your daughter.
Yeah. They said you'd say that.
Who? Look, I don't know
what you're talking about.
I know that you
and the rest of the 4,400
trick innocent people.
I read all about it
on the 44orum.
You manipulated me,
claiming to be my daughter.
Kevin Wellington was right.
The 4,400 are just posing
as long-lost family members
and then killing them.
No, that's not what...
How can I...
Remember when you took
me and Mom to the botanicals
when I was eight?
And I gave Mom
a really hard time
because I wanted to wear
that white dress,
the one she was saving
for Easter.
And you made me wear this,
like, horrid bright
orange shirt.
And I was so mad, until we got
to the butterfly enclosure.
And then out of nowhere,
all the, all the butterflies
started flocking to my shirt
till I was covered
in butterflies.
And then I wasn't mad anymore.
It was the first time you
called me your little butterfly.
Not all the powers are bad.
And Mildred only did
what she did because...
they treated her horribly
at this facility, Ypsi Med.
But we're still us.
Look, I'm-I'm still me.
I'm still your little butterfly.
It was a nice try,
but I know you're not
my daughter.
You stole her memories somehow,
and you're trying to
use them against me.
But I know the truth,
and you are not human.
If you won't show
your true self,
then I'll just have to make you.
Dad!
All right, in most cases,
the pawn is considered
the weakest on the board.
But, if it reaches the other
side without being captured,
it can be promoted to any other
chess piece except a king.
Okay. Okay. Pawn promotion.
I think I got that.
Yeah. Yeah, it's pretty cool.
But good luck getting your pawn
past my defense.
Oh... All right.
So, wh-what happened
with the landscaping contract
for Hockeytown Properties?
I mean, Ms. Bridget said
you didn't get the job.
Yeah, um...
You know, they-they pulled out
last minute,
decided to go with someone else.
Yeah, is it because you were
on TV supporting us,
then Mildred tried
to kill Bill Greene?
Now she's on these posters...
I'm scared of
what she might do next,
or what she might
get others to do.
Look, either way,
I'm sorry she caused you
to lose work.
Maybe it had nothing to do
with Mildred.
It's as much a mystery to me
as chess.
Look, I'm just glad
that you decided not to go
back to that hotel.
It's not where I feel
like I belong anymore.
You know? But I also feel safe
here with you all.
That you are.
All right, so now
I-I can do this, yeah?
Okay, let's try this again.
What?
We can work here
undisturbed now.
I must show you
what the COBOL code found.
Apparently, the government was
looking for something called.
ZMT in our blood.
ZMT? Never heard of it.
Neither had I.
We'll figure out what it is.
Now that you're back,
I'm confident we'll solve
this mystery in no time.
If you wish to discuss it,
I shall listen.
Who's there?
Sorry. Sorry.
Uh, I didn't think anyone else
was going to come in here.
I'm Jorge,
a 4,400 friend of Jharrel's.
He never mentioned you.
You know,
I'm gonna go get Shanice,
and she'll let us know
if you're one of us
or a 44orem-er trying
to sneak in.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
All right, the truth is
I'm Manny, Jharrel's brother.
I'm a 4,400 just like you.
The government is after me,
and I'm hiding here because it's
the only place that's safe.
W-Wait, you're,
like, Manny-Manny?
Jharrel must be so pleased
you're back.
Did he tell you?
We found the COBOL code
among your books.
No.
Then spill the tea. Yes.
What is ZMT,
and how is it connected
to us being zapped here?
I know it's in our blood,
but please tell us,
does it explain how we got here,
or why we have powers?
ZMT is the reason
I'm afraid for my life.
What does that mean?
The answers that
you think you want
are only gonna lead
to the deaths
of people that you love.
So, for their sake
and the sake of the other 4,400,
let this ZMT thing go
and forget you ever saw me.
And there are
these apps that let you
send money to people and ones
that can tell you the time
on the other side of the world.
Can you believe that?
Hey, stranger.
Glad to see you survived
your time on the inside.
I was worried about you.
Thanks.
But I just want to put
the whole thing behind me.
Please say that
you changed your mind
and you're gonna come stay here
in the hotel.
That ain't for me,
you know that.
But I am happy to bring Mildred
back here, though.
All right, fine.
Maybe you could mix me up
a drink sometime.
Show off what you learned
at that bartending convention.
I'm sure we could figure
something out.
All right, cool.
All right, what gives?
You are happier
than a dog with two tails,
and it can't be just
'cause you're glad to see me.
Okay. Yes.
It's my brother. He's back.
Well, I'll be.
I mean, he's all
you've been talking about,
not to mention
I'm staying at his place.
I need to thank him in person.
I promise not to bite.
Have you connected with anyone
from the time you left?
I've reached out to my son,
Quincy,
hoping we could find
some common ground.
But I haven't heard from him.
Whatever happens, the 4,400
are my children now.
That's the one who...
She hurt that man. Mildred?
What is she doing here?
Brother Harold, your nerves
are understandable,
but I can assure you,
Mildred is one of us.
Sister Mildred.
In from the cold
and fully transformed.
The guy looked really terrified.
Do you think it'll be okay
if I just come back?
Many understand how badly
the government treated us,
some worse than others.
I understand
what Bill Greene did to you,
why you did what you did.
Thank you for stopping me.
Still, I want my powers back.
Can you do that?
I'm not sure exactly
how it works yet,
but I'll try.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, I guess.
I know he's
Jharrel's brother, but...
I'm not inclined to trust
someone we just met
with decisions
that could affect us all.
I don't trust him either, but...
I don't think ZMT is what really
matters right now, Andre.
You don't know
what it's like out there.
The things people believe
about us, it is scary.
Look, that's why I'm here
and not with my mom.
You all are my family.
And I came here to warn you
that danger is real,
and it's immediate.
What happened?
In Miami?
I saw what's out there
firsthand.
I saw that anyone
can turn against you
because they've been brainwashed
by this nonsense.
What nonsense exactly?
That we're iguanas.
That we're imposters.
That we'll steal their souls
in the night.
That we'll eat their babies.
None of it is real
or makes any sense.
They will believe anything
that excuses
their irrational hatred of us.
Whatever narrative works
for them.
We're not human to them.
And how can we reason with them
if that's what they think?
There it is.
Wow.
It really does look like her
from the pictures
you've shown me.
Daddy, who is this?
Shane,
he's a vet friend of mine.
Does a lot of work
with exotic animals.
He's gonna help me figure out
what happened to my daughter.
I am your daughter.
We both know you're not.
Oh, my God.
But you're gonna tell me
what you did with her.
Don't worry. We'll get
to the truth,
one way or the other.
Oh. Oh, boy, oh, boy. Ah!
Manny?
You can come out now.
Jharrel.
I asked you to keep
my whereabouts to yourself.
I know,
but you don't really say no
to Claudette.
I heard a lot about you.
It's nice to finally meet you.
It's nice to meet you, too.
Well, as much
as I'd love to stay,
I have to get going.
My shift's starting soon.
Okay, well, I'll catch you
after the wedding.
Yeah.
Would you look at that.
Yeah?
I guess we're both
learning a lot.
Huh, Jorge?
One of the greats.
It's a shame
most people nowadays
have no idea who he was.
I'm Jorge.
I'm not in the mood to chat.
All right, I'll be quick,
Claudette.
Don't worry.
I'm pro-4,400.
I heard about how you ousted
that anti-4,400 bartender
and I thought
there's more
that I could teach you.
Teach me?
You're wasting your time.
I don't need your help.
Revolutions of the past started
in church basements
and closed quarters.
Now we mobilize out in the open.
I want to level
the playing field.
Teach you how to use
modern skills of resistance
and organization.
Help you hone your powers.
No one's gonna give
the 4,400 their freedom,
their power.
You've got to take it.
It's what Stokely believed.
Come to one of our meetings,
see what you think.
If you like it,
you can come train with me
for a few weeks.
Think about it.
Claudette. Claudette, wait.
What the hell, Jorge?
Manny? Whoever you claim to be.
Did Jharrel see you run
out here? What does he think...
He got a call to come pick up
the marriage license.
Listen, I can explain.
Explain what?
That you lied to me?
A-And now, you're lying
to your brother,
letting him think
we've never met before.
Jharrel is not ready
to hear the truth.
Not like you. So now you
want me to lie to him, too?
Oh, you have got some nerve.
You have every right
to be angry with me.
But don't let this distract you
from the movement.
Look, I saw
the posters you put up.
Using that telekinetic girl,
that was genius.
That's what we need,
a rallying call,
for people to see her power.
She doesn't have her power
anymore. Rev took it away.
He can take powers away.
But she is still a symbol,
even without her power.
She was brave enough
to fight for our freedom.
Which is exactly why
you need to stay focused.
The 4,400 need you.
Even if that means
not telling Jharrel the truth.
What are you so hyped up about?
It just so happens that
I have some hot tea to sip.
Jharrel's brother, Manny,
is alive, and staying here,
in the hotel.
Manny? Mm-hmm.
But...
LaDonna and I stumbled upon him
in the cocktail lounge earlier.
And get this, he's a 4,400, too.
Wow.
Well, Jharrel must be thrilled
to have him back.
Can't wait to meet him.
Uh, does he need a room?
Well, I'm not sure
you'll be able
to meet him just yet.
His return is supposed to be
on the down low.
More wedding planning, I see.
Just when I think
I'm almost done,
I get another request
from the happy couple.
It must be hard,
watching this joyful reunion.
I'm sure it's
stirring up feelings
about your own family.
About Logan.
Well, it's not that, exactly.
I'm exhausted
from wedding planning
and running the hotel.
I just...
I don't feel
like I have a choice.
And sometimes I wish
I could just be free
of all of it, you know.
My-my life before seemed...
easier, you know?
Well, I'm here to help
with whatever you need.
You just say the word, okay?
Thank you, Andre. Hmm.
You're one of
the bright spots in all of this.
I know what might
lift your spirits.
Would you do me the honor
of accompanying me
to tonight's festivities?
It would make me
the luckiest man there.
Outside of Ji-Eun's betrothed,
of course.
I would love to.
All right, let's try this again.
We both know I haven't gotten
any better since last time.
Look, chess is all about
pushing your opponent
to a corner
without them realizing it
until it's too late.
All right.
What are you doing, bud?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
What in the world?
I just feel like this huge
weight has been lifted.
I can only imagine.
Is he gonna want his place back?
I don't...
know what he wants.
You know, I just want him here.
So, he told you he's a 4,400
just like us?
Yeah, I'm still trying to wrap
my brain around everything.
Trying to, I don't know,
be a good brother.
Trust him.
I was hard on him in the past.
Just be careful, okay?
W-What the 4,400 went through...
it changed us.
Manny may be dealing
with more than he's telling you.
You ready?
Tell me.
When a child hurts themself,
they only know they're hurt
because of how
the adults around them react.
Pain is learned,
and it can be unlearned.
If I want full control
of my powers,
I have to unlearn the pain.
It is the only way
to open my mind
to what is possible.
To embrace what only you can do.
Remember, the 44orum-ers are not
gonna stop coming after you.
This...
this is how you
protect yourself.
What do you feel?
Nothing.
Good.
Now it's time
to return to your life
and prepare the others
for the coming fight.
It's up to you to get
the word out for the 4,400.
Tell them to embrace
their power.
Everything else will
fall into place.
So, you're gonna tell me
who you really are?
You're way too connected to have
returned like the rest of us.
You're right.
I'm not a 4,400.
Well, then who are you?
And why are you so invested
in what happens to us?
For now, all you need to know is
that I'm here on
a different mission.
I'll tell you more about it,
when the time is right.
Thank you. You're welcome.
All right,
you sure you want to do this?
You know that Bridget,
Mariah and I want you
to live with us, right?
Look, it's safer for everyone.
Look, if anything happened
to any of you, I...
I wouldn't be able to live
with myself.
Hayden!
You're back!
Mildred, you're here.
Did you come for the wedding?
The wedding?
Oh, who's getting married?
Ji-Eun and Harold.
Okay, um...
No, I, uh,
I'm just bringing Hayden back.
Well, you have to stay,
Mr. Kaminski.
The more, the merrier.
Yeah, please, stay.
I-If it's not too much trouble.
All right. I'll go move the car.
I missed you, Hay.
How are you? Tell me everything.
Come on!
Go! Yes, yeah!
Right there! Right there.
Put 'em up, put 'em up.
Yeah...! Lesbi-Pins!
Woo-hoo!
Bam, put 'em up!
Did you see that?
I wasn't sure I was
in the right place.
Oh, I know. It's okay.
It's hard to believe that
I'm a cryptologist,
triple agent
and an athlete,
all in my spare time.
Wait, does bowling count
as a sport?
Hell yeah, it does.
What's wrong with you?
Called you here
'cause it was loud.
We're less likely
to be recorded,
and I'm sticking to my routine...
Less red flags that way.
And your schedule involves
the Lesbi-Pins?
Don't tell me you're more of a
Motor City Rollers kind of guy.
More of a Feather Bowler.
That's acceptable.
Hey.
Thank you for helping me
find my brother.
Uh, you are an evil genius.
I know.
How are you handling
all this cloak-and-dagger?
I know it's got to be tough.
Yeah.
I realized I had to do
everything I could to help.
My mom doesn't want me sticking
my neck out, but...
it's the hard decisions
that matter, right?
Amen to that.
And listen, after
what Jessica put you through,
I had to find out
what happened to Manny,
why he was so important,
why the government was hell-bent
on finding him.
That's 'cause he refused
to work for them.
Not exactly.
That's why I needed
to talk to you.
Manny's work involved
something called ZMT.
The government thinks
that it's connected
to what makes the 4,400 so...
unique.
Okay, w-wait.
What are you saying?
'Cause Manny got zapped
and appeared on Belle Isle,
like everybody else. J...
He's not telling you everything.
The government's looking for
Manny because they need him,
because he knows something about
how the 4,400 just showed up,
which means that he knows more
about all of this
than he's been letting on.
Ji-Eun. Harold.
Your love story is
a parable for us all.
Ji-Eun, are you ready
for me to strip you of your powers?
I am.
It worked.
Your power is gone.
Thank you for giving me
my life back.
Now there's only one more thing
for us to do.
Just need both of
your signatures
on your marriage license.
Then, we can get
to your wedding.
I can't wait to be your husband.
The ceremony was groovy.
Ji-Eun and Harold seemed
so happy.
And thank you for helping me
pick out this outfit.
That's what roomies do,
right? They, I don't know,
lend each other clothes
and have movie nights.
Speaking of which,
we really do need to do, like,
a proper Drew Barrymore binge.
Trust me, you're gonna love her.
You know what, and honestly,
it's-it's really good to be back
and living with somebody
who I can actually trust.
And we can all face
whatever's coming together.
Almost all of us.
I know my sister's at Ypsi Med,
and I'm not giving up
until I free her.
Hey, Jharrel.
Hey.
See the cake I made
for the happy couple?
I still got it.
It's dope.
It better be.
Took me two days
to make that thing,
and trying to get it over here
without ruining it...
Now I just need the knife
to cut the cake.
I swear I brought it down here,
but...
Anyway,
where's Manny?
I'm excited to meet him.
I actually can't find him.
I don't know
where he would've gone,
and I really need
to talk to him.
I'm sure he's around here
somewhere.
Wow.
Aw, Logan.
So glad you could join us
for this special occasion.
Oh, yeah, man. You know,
it's nice seeing everybody
in such good spirits.
I couldn't agree more.
I'll go grab us some drinks.
How are you holding up?
It's-it's been a lot.
Between managing the-the hotel
and planning this weeding,
I haven't really had
a moment to myself.
Like, is this it?
Is this my life now?
Are you kidding me?
You're managing this whole place
by yourself,
and you're doing
a damn good job at it.
Yeah, I just don't know
who I am anymore.
You're still you.
You've always wanted
to help people,
and that's exactly
what you're doing.
What you're doing is important.
This is... Our wedding song.
You want to dance?
Nah, I'm not sure we should...
Come on.
One dance.
What?
You were always such a mushball
at weddings.
I'm glad to see
that hasn't changed.
Yeah.
They seem like the real deal.
I'm rooting for them.
Yeah, me, too.
Is there something
I can help you with?
I know what you did.
I'm not sure I'm following.
You stripped me of my power.
And I want it back.
You said you weren't...
I don't know how to do that.
You knew that already,
didn't you?
Maybe.
But what was
that thing you said?
"All things are possible
to him who believeth."
What do you believe, Isaiah?
What?
Excuse me. I just...
I-I have to...
All right, ready?
One, two, three.
I'll do one this way.
And one, two, three.
What?
I know this is hard to believe,
but this is
for the greater good.
- What the...?
- Oh, my God.
Rev. Rev!
Can you hear me?
Rev.
Stay with me, Rev.
Captioning sponsored by CBS.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org