It's been 48 hours since
Special Agent William Greene,
a high-level
government official,
was seen being thrown out
of Detroit's
Bois Blanc Hotel window
by this mere girl.
She has been identified
as Mildred Bell,
last seen in
Sebastopol, California
in 1972.
But what's really gripped us all
was the fact that Miss Bell
committed this horrendous
act of violence
telekinetically.
Ever since they
landed on Belle Isle
seven weeks ago,
the 4,400 have been
in the public's eye
and imagination.
And we were there,
broadcasting to you live,
as our cameras
captured the secret
they've been hiding all along.
What you've seen on your screens
over the last 48 hours
demands answers
and has led many of us
to ask the question:
Are any of us truly safe?
Do you remember where you were,
what you were doing,
when you first saw
the revelation
of their destructive powers?
And we are back.
Live from the Bois Blanc Hotel.
I'm gonna circle back
on our friend Bruno.
Make sure he hasn't
gone full pyro.
All right, bet.
But from what he said.
He didn't want to go along
with the government's plan
to make the 4,400look bad
any more than we
wanted it to happen.
Okay, and I believe that,
but I don't know what kind of
accidental damages might occur
when someone can shoot fire
from their hands, so...
What the hell?
- All hands on deck.
Let's go, let's go. Move, move.
Hey!
What happened?
There was an incident
in the courtyard.
And we are back.
Live from the Bois Blanc Hotel.
I am happy to introduce you
to the first truly blended 4,400
and 2021 family.
We have husband and wife,
Logan Kaminski
and Bridget Templeton,
their beautiful daughter Mariah,
and Hayden Turner, the 4,400
they have welcomed
into their home.
Hi, everybody.
Hi. Hi.
Thanks, Gladys. We're just so
happy to have been able
to invite Hayden
into our home. Hey, Jess.
What you watching?
Dana.
Hi. Um...
Look, about the
other night, I...
I... didn't mean to... I mean,
I-I just got out of kind of
a pretty serious relationship,
so I-I shouldn't have...
No sweat, Tanner.
I needed to blow off
some steam, too. Hot chocolate,
shot of espresso. Thank you.
Uh, you know, having Hayden
in our home...
Agent Tanner. Hi, Bill.
Patient 32 is confirmed
and standing by at location.
Everything looks like
it's going well...
Well, it's not.
Our fire starter
is somehow AWOL.
We have people trying
to look for him, but...
Wait, what do you mean
he's AWOL?
What're we supposed to do?
How could you lose him?
We have names.
Bill?
Who is that? Is...
What's going on?
Is that Patient 48?
Oh, that's not-not me.
Another 4,400.
She's, like, so awesome.
Oh, my God.
And we are back. Live from the
Bois Blanc Hotel. I'm happy
to introduce you...
How can they give
these freaks airtime?
4,400...
Yo, Steve.
Hilarious, right? Come on.
Dude, they're...
they're not that bad.
How about this one?
Whoa. The hell was that?
All hands
on deck. All hands on deck.
Courtyard compromised.
Cover this corridor
and wait for further orders.
Come on. Let's go, let's go.
Move, move.
Officer needs assistance.
Bill Greene was thrown
from a third-story window.
She tried to kill him.
Stop.
Brother, calm now.
We need to pray for Bill.
Courtyard, courtyard.
And we are back.
And Neela's got the twins, too.
She's an ER doctor now.
Beti.
I'm tired of being the only
boomer at Jummah
with a single daughter.
They're asking questions.
"Oh, Aamira, when is Soraya
bringing home
one of those Goris?"
You know what? It doesn't
matter, Mom. All good.
It does matter.
You work too much as it is.Okay.
You owe them nothing.
Not those 4,400s
or those other people
you work for.
You've been in service
how many years?
And they detain you
like some terrorist,
when we know
for a fact the real terrorists
in this country
are the ones who look like them.
Ma. Oh, my God.
Seriously? You're gonna
get me in trouble.
And I'm proud of your work. I
see this whole event on the TV,
this nice family, it all looks
very big and important,
but I want you to stay safe.
I only care about you.
Okay, Ma.
Oh, Soraya!
Up. Up in the window.
What the actual hell?
You kept me a prisoner...
It's clear that the 4,400
have been hiding their
true nature from the world.
What could they want from us?
And what kind of threat
do they pose?
Right now,
officials cannot explain
what is happening
in these frightening images,
and so we must remember
how things were.
Because after this
monumental revelation,
nothing will ever
be the same again.
You kept me a prisoner
for no reason...
Federal and local governments
have set up a tip line
for the public to call,
asking for your help to report
any suspicious activity.
We're joined now live
from D.C. by Justin François
with the latest
on these events...
Which is why we will now
be triggering
the conservatorships
we already have in place.
What about our safety?
How is that gonna help?
How can you even enforce that?
Obviously, a number
of the 4,400 are already
integrated to the general
public, out on their own,
but the government
knows where they are,
and the tip line allows
for any citizen to call in
if they have any suspicious
activity relating to them.
Why not just round them up?
Because, legally speaking,
we do not have justification
to detain them, yet.
However, those 4,400
who have signed our contracts
will now be placed
under our conservatorship,
for everyone's safety.
Until we know more, they will be
held at the hotel with no
outside contact.
That means no more phones,
or access to the Internet.
They'll be subjected
to a new regimen
of medical care and testing,
and all information obtained
will be the property
of the federal government.
They will be sequestered
in the Bois Blanc,
until further notice,
subject to questioning,
and their movement within
this facility will be monitored.
Guards are authorized
to use force
if necessary.
Are you okay?
I'm so sorry.
The conservatorships
give them the legal right. I...
I don't know what we can do.
So, we're back
to being prisoners.
Some of us more than others.
Okay, this is beyond messed up.
A tip line only
encourages people
to further demonize the 4,400,
and you saw firsthand
at the bar with Claudette
how bad it was
before the world knew.
True, but we all saw
Mildred's little demonstration.
Honestly, I'm surprised
the government
isn't responding more severely.
Yeah, because that's
exactly what they planned
for it to be.
Look, Mildred only did
what Bruno was supposed to do,
reveal their powers
to the world,
and your girlfriend already knew
about those powers, remember?
Ex. Ex-girlfriend.
Yeah, whatever. Mildred is dangerous.
It doesn't take a bunch
of 4,400 with powers
to do some real damage.
It just takes one.
The government has to protect
the public. Oh, come on.
Anybody can be dangerous,
but giving paranoid people
a reason to profile the 4,400,
using this conservatorship BS
to take their rights away,
this is how
a police state works,
and you know it.
You're oversimplifying
the situation.
I'm not.
Things are getting bad,
which is why I wanted
to show you this.
Yeah, I remember.
You and your brother
doodle a clock.
You take turns
putting in numbers.
Yes. Look, Manny is here,
doing this somehow,
playing the game again.
I put this two up weeks ago.
And that six just
showed up, but...
It should be a three.
So, it's wrong?
Jharrel, what does
this have to do with...
Yes, it's wrong, but I think
that's because Manny's trying
to tell me something.
Jharrel, anyone
could've done this.
A bored employee.
A 4,400 with a power or a pen.
Or my brother,
who might be involved
with all of this somehow.
The timing alone... I mean,
this showed up right before
everything went down.
Look, you didn't know him,
all right,
but Manny was...
he was brilliant.
He saw the world differently.
I think that Manny's
trying to reach me.
Ji-Eun,
it's gonna be all right.
You're not the one
who's wearing these clothes.
You didn't sign the contract.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
I can't be held prisoner again.
After everything we've already lost...
Are you okay?
I just want to go back.
To my family, to my friends,
to Harold.
I thought it could be
okay, but this...
I miss my family, too.
My old life.
I just got
a Jack Russell Terrier. Haneul.
He was super sweet.
I bet he was a handful...
but I bet you took
great care of him.
This is all so overwhelming,
but it doesn't have to
overrun us.
Think of Haneul next time.
Okay? Okay.
Thank you, Shanice.
I hate them for
doing this to us.
You holding up all right?
Thank you for helping her.
I just...
I've never not known
what to say.
I should be able
to lead these people.
It's my fault
that this has happened.
Why didn't you sign
one of those contracts?
To be honest, I was more focused
on the task at hand.
I was working
in tandem with Bill,
keeping people safe, protected.
I never thought that...
If only I'd
got to him before Mildred.
Still, you saved his life
by stopping her.
The only thing that matters
is moving forward.
We have to figure out
how to fix this.
Come in.
Since when do they knock?
Uh, hi.
Word on the street
was you wanted to see me?
You must be Soraya?
The very one.
What's up?
LaDonna said you helped her
build this computer,
and that if I ever
needed anything,
I could reach out to you,
and I haven't heard from her
for a few days now,
and... Uh, same, actually.
Hm. Seems we've both
been ghosts.
Oh. Uh, "ghosted."
"Ghosted."
Hmm. But this can't wait.
I must know if anything we found
at Ypsi Med helps us understand
what the government
wants from us.
I live in fear of the guards
finding this.
I'm at an impasse.
I can see the files,
but there are so many of them,
and I don't know
what I'm looking for.
And I managed to finally type in
all of Manny's COBOL code,
but what to do next...
Uh, I am so sorry.
Uh, but...
you, LaDonna, Mildred,
you can all...
You know what,
it's not important.
You want to know
if we all have powers,
and what they are.
It doesn't matter.
I know firsthand
what that feels like,
being asked endless questions.
I'm sorry.
I was being rude.
Just know that I am
no danger to you.
You can trust me. Trust us.
You understand what that says?
Uh, some parts, yeah.
Basically, it was written
to analyze and compartmentalize
large data sets.
Like the patient files
we got from Ypsi Med?
Exactly.
But we've got to run it
through a compiler,
which I think our girl LaDonna
forgot to install.
And you could do that?
Yeah. I can download a compiler
and do a quick install.
I'll come find you when we're
ready to run this sucker.
Run?
Where will we be running?
Yo, you wanted to see me?
Uh, yes. Thank you for coming.
I just wanted to
let you know that
you are fired.
Effective immediately.
Thank you for your service.
Wow. So it's like that?
You know, I figured things
might be changing around here
for all of us,
but nope, just me, huh?
You have been a pain in my ass
from the minute
you entered this facility.
You've broken numerous rules.
You assisted in the attempted
escape of 32...
You mean Bruno Comtois?
They have names, Jessica.
So will you be needing
a police escort or...
You really want to
play this game?
See, because I know what
y'all are up to at Ypsi Med.
So you can fire me all you want,
but what is to keep me
from telling the truth?
Huh? From going to the press?
Call Gladys Keller
for all I care.
You would actually be
doing me a favor.
After Mildred's little display,
the public is just waiting
for confirmation
that all the 4,400 have powers.
And when they get that,
they'll be begging for us
to protect them.
We shine when we serve
and protect. Remember?
You're gonna regret being
on this side
of history, Jessica.
I have an idea.Please.
Well, it's really an idea
we already had.
Your sermon a few weeks ago?
Our call for sanctuary.
We need to finish
what we started.
We need to make this hotel
a religious sanctuary
for all of the 4,400,
and for real this time.
No more government deals.
Believe me, lesson learned.
When sanctuary is granted,
it would nullify
these conservatorships.
The government wouldn't
even be able to
step foot in here.
And I already finished
a lot of the paperwork
before you struck your deal
with Bill Greene.
But creating a church here,
it was predicated
on my being their leader, right?
And I just don't know.
Ever since... Mildred.
Right?
You were up there with her.
You've seemed... off ever since.
Did something happen
when you were with her?
I pulled her away
from the window
to try to stop her, and...
when I let go,
her powers were gone.
What do you mean, "gone"?
She tried to use
her powers on me,
but she couldn't.
She couldn't.
And as I've thought about it,
I've come to realize that
perhaps this is my power.
To negate the powers
of others and...
You can take away powers?
It can't be!
I champion that
which makes us special.
Our powers, our abilities.
What does it mean
if I can take it all away?
What kind of leader
can I be for them?
I can't.
Here is to lasting
as long as I did.
Mm. 'Cause Lord knows
she wanted me gone
since day one.
Yeah, I did have to save
your ass a few times.
Yeah, well,
now she dumped us both.
No, something changed.
Okay? She's not the same as
she was when this all started.
Or she is, and you are
just seeing things
more clearly now.
Hmm. You mean your way.
Well, my way does collect
unemployment now, so...
Hey, at least
I'm still there, huh?
Run interference between
Jessica and the 4,400.
You think you can keep
your girl in check? Mm.
How many times
do I have to tell you
she is not my girl, Jharrel?
You sure about that?
'Cause I caught her looking
at you this morning during
what turned out to be
my farewell briefing.
Anyway, now that I am banned
from the Bois Blanc,
do you think you can, like,
I don't know,
at least keep an eye
on the clock for me?
You know, take photos, uh,
text me if anything new appears.
Jharrel, if he was trying
to talk to you,
why not just go, like,
"Bloop, here I am, bro.
And-and here's
your urgent message."
I don't know.
Okay? Maybe he's in
danger or something,
and that's why
he hasn't appeared.
But that mark showed up
right when everything
went to hell.
Look, I can't believe that
that means nothing.
You have a better explanation
for any of the stuff
that's been going on these days?
All right, fine.
I'll keep an eye
on your damn wall.
Thanks, partner.
And this next round is
going on my Chime card.
Hey. What can I get you?
It feels like a distant
memory, the fresh air.
Glad to see no one has
discovered our tunnel
into the free world.
Yeah, you're right, but
I hope no one sees us.
That tip line has me spooked.
Since Mildred's display,
it's as if the whole world
is just waiting for one of us
to spontaneously combust.
Hmm. Well, our powers,
it is all a lot to take in.
And especially difficult
given our lack of privacy.
I was with Rev earlier
when he confided in me
that he thinks when
he grabbed Mildred
up in that office,
he took away her powers.
What does this mean?
That with the slightest touch
he can absorb
or relieve us of our powers? I don't know.
But it is something
he's processing right now.
And I know you, Andre.
Give him some time
before you go all
scientific method on him.
Well, to be honest, I have
other pressing concerns.
And, I'm happy to report,
we have a new ally.
What? Mm-hmm.
Who?
There's a woman,
a tech-spert named Soraya,
who's helping us
look into these files.
If we can make sense
of all of this...
then maybe we can find
a way forward.
Hey.
We gotta go.
What are you doing?
Oh, no.
No, Andre. People may see.
He needs help, Shanice.
God! Holy mothballs, this hurts!
You okay?
Steve, let me just...
What the... Andre, let's go now.
This is exactly what
I was afraid of.
That person near us was
for sure calling that tip line.
What if they come for us, Andre?
Take you to Ypsi Med?
I couldn't leave Steve
in pain like that.
When you take an oath
to help people,
you can't choose your patients.
We aren't on the front lines
of a war, Andre.
Nor are you practicing
in a hospital.
You do have a choice
in who you heal right now,
because it impacts more
than just yourself.
Ever since we came here
and got these powers,
it has only caused pain,
suffering.
Made our lives more difficult.
We have been othered in
so many different ways, Andre.
And now this? They also help.
I can heal.
Your power has aided me
in the past.
But to what end?
You heal somebody,
but that makes you sick.
You're only gonna get sicker
unless you find some way
to release whatever is inside.
True.
But I doubt Claudette
would be up for
a damaged knee, even if
she were in town.
Andre, this isn't a joke.
Shanice, fair warning.
There's a rat behind you.
What?!
Perhaps a solution.
Andre!
Oh. It worked.
Damn. Nothing from Jess?
I guess I gotta get used to her,
what, not texting me back?
You know what,
I know that I have been
hard on you about it,
but I really am sorry
that you two broke up.
Are you?
Hey, girl.
Soraya. Hello.
So I missed,
uh, raising a glass
to your untimely demise.
Hey, you got it worse than me.
They made you keep your job.
Okay.
Is it weird for you that
Jessica canned your partner?
Uh, we just killed a bottle
trying to figure that out.
But, uh, the answer is no.
I mean, it's unacceptable.
She needs to be called out
for her behavior.
Okay. Attagirl.
See, J, you still got a partner.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
That wasn't here before.
Manny was here.
Huh. He did this.
It's like the one you
showed me in the hotel,
but there's a one, two,
six, nine.
Oh, God, don't encourage him.
Come on, Keisha.
Like he knew that I got fired.
That is why
he left the clue here.
Why wouldn't he
just reveal himself?
Why-why go through
these hoops? Preach.
Something must be wrong.
I don't know, maybe
he's in trouble or...
Maybe it's just
the Quantico speaking,
but if it is Manny...
And I'm not saying it is...
Maybe he's trying
to get a message across.
Like, maybe those numbers
correspond to letters.
Maybe it's a cypher.
You need to figure out
what the key is.
Something you would both know.
A cypher.
I mean, it'd be
more Manny's thing.
I-I wouldn't even know
where to start.
Well, maybe he's putting
his faith in you
to know him a little better
than you think you do.
Okay, um...
Oh, we would leave
clocks in books
that we would read together.
Maybe there's something
on page 1,269.
I mean, I don't know
if we read anything that long,
but thank you.
Want to stay?
Round on me.
I should go home.
I already know I got
a long day tomorrow.
Ah, no more patellar
disturbances I hope.
Don't come near me.
Keep your distance.
Steve, what's wrong? Does your knee...
Because of your little stunt,
some park rando thought
I was one of you. A 4,400.
Not only did she call
the tip line,
she put my picture online,
and I got doxxed.
Okay? And now I have people
harassing my family's
storefront again.
You're not gonna be
another reason
me and my family have
targets on our backs.
But you were in
so much distress,
and I know Miss LaDonna
would have wanted me
looking after... Don't
even talk about LaDonna!
Stay away from me.
You are aware that
these conservatorships
don't apply to us?
We're not prisoners,
and you can't keep us...
Did you two try to exit the
premises despite it being
very clear we need to keep you
here for your own safety?
We would like to cross
the street to mail something.
We have every right to leave.
Any unlawful detainment... Like I said,
it's not detainment,
it's public safety.
I'll take whatever it is.
Oh, no, ma'am.
We're not gonna rely
on you for anything.
I've tried that.
Look where it got us.
In fact, we are filing papers
to make this space a sanctuary.
This time, you're not
gonna stop us.
Well, I hate
to burst your bubble,
but you'll need refugee status,
which is granted
by my department,
DHS, in order to be
given sanctuary
anywhere in the city of Detroit,
or anywhere else,
for that matter.
And we have filed
a comprehensive,
legally sound motion
to be granted such status
as refugees out of time.
That is very clever.
But there's a lot of red tape
with this kind of thing,
and we kind of have
our hands full,
as you might have noticed.
So it doesn't really matter
if you make it to the mailbox
or not.
Your whole gambit is pointless.
Keisha.
Hi.
What are you... You fired Jharrel?
Your friend Jharrel has been
a pain in my ass
since day one,
undermining my authority.
I can't have that kind of
insubordination on my watch.
Men think they rule the world.
He's a good social worker.
He actually cares...
And you seem to care more
about me letting him go
than about our breakup.
I miss you.
How can you say that?
When you're keeping these
people detained in this hotel?
You want to talk
about your feelings?
You're treating them
like animals.
I'm treating them
like the threat they are.
Explain to me why
all of their blood panels came
back with matching anomalies?
I've seen firsthand the "people"
that we have at Ypsi Med,
like a man who can shoot fire,
who we thankfully contained,
or Mildred, for that matter,
who is still at large.
We've already gotten
over 200 phone calls
off the tip line.
Well, why now?
You've already known about
their powers, about Ypsi Med.
Due to Gladys Keller's
broadcast,
we finally have the public
on our side.
A public that wants to know
that we are managing
a potential danger to society.
A public that deserves
to feel safe and protected.
You wanted this to happen.
For people to feel scared.
Come on, Jess,
don't be that person.
I'm who I've always been.
You're the one that's changed.
I've grown.
You can, too.
With a stroke of your pen,
you could stop this absurdity,
actually let the 4,400
have a proper sanctuary here.
Just let them be.
Honestly, I'm surprised
that this is your position.
Your sister was murdered
because of someone
that shouldn't have been out
and was lethally dangerous.
Don't do that.
You don't bring my sister
into this mess,
like it changes the fact
that what you're doing...
No, Keisha, what we'redoing.
What we're doing...
is wrong.
I quit.
So, this compiler
is cross-referencing
all those Ypsi Med files
with the COBOL code.
I just hope that whatever this
compiler says
frees us from suspicions.
Even Steve,
who's usually quite
keen and amiable,
accosted me over...
Soraya, this tip line,
what's it for?
Well...
mostly, it's to
instill fear,
create a chilling effect.
It weaponizes every person
on the street, with all their
misinformation and prejudices
and... hate.
But Steve? How could he think...
Anyone is susceptible,
given the right conditions.
We all have to protect
ourselves sometimes,
especially those of us
who stick out.
I'm sure this past year wasn't
easy for Steve and his family.
The anti-Asian hate
during COVID, it was awful,
and it still is.
I'm not saying
he's right, I just...
He's scared,
just like you are.
This whole thing is just not
as simple as we'd like it to be.
What's it say?
What's it all mean?
Looks like the code has isolated
a particular property
found in 4,400 blood.
Something called... ZMT?
This is probably why
the mandated blood draws...
What is it?
I never practiced
with this knowledge,
nor do I recall any ZMT
appearing in any of the recent
literature I've been reading.
What could this mean?
I don't know, but...
Do you trust me?
Can I look into this for you?
For the 4,400?
Of course. An ally of LaDonna's
is mine as well.
How is it that, lately, I've led
my people down
such an atrocious path?
I have their best
interests at heart,
but every action,
every decision I've made
has been the wrong one.
And on top of all that,
my power, it's...
It's of no use.
I'm literally
making us powerless
with a single touch.
I disagree.
It's why I came to talk to you.
I want you
to take away my power.
What? But why?
You call it my power,
but I feel... burdened.
I'm terrified to touch anyone,
even those closest to me,
or maybe those closest
to me most of all,
and-and I... we
never had a say in any of this.
These powers, they're gifts
from God, Shanice.
You've helped people,
even Ji-Eun the other day.
She didn't ask me to.
And she didn't know.
I didn't know it would happen.
It-It's invasive.
It's wrong.
But that doesn't
give me the right.
I can't just take it from you.
No, no, Your power isn't about
taking something away,
it's about
providing us with something
we were never given,
a choice.
And I can give you that,
But the Lord didn't bring us
here to flounder alone.
He gave us each other
and he gave...
Did it work?
Yes.
It did.
Thank you.
I think it's finally gone.
I snuck out and
mailed the paperwork
in for the sanctuary anyway,
because... well, you never know.
But if it's the powers
that gave the government
the right to trigger
the conservatorships,
maybe we could file appeals
for those who choose...
to get rid of them.Yeah.
Might take away their
justification for their...
- DHS property goes.
- Leave everything else.
Can you believe this?
The government is just leaving.
How did you manage this?
I don't... I don't know... Ah, my favorite
co-conspirators.
Glad I caught you.
Here. Congratulations.
You've forced my hand
and made the hotel a sanctuary.
My department will be contesting
this new designation in court,
of course, you'll be tied up
in litigation for months, but
for now, it's all yours.
They gave us our refugees
through time status.
Why would she do this?
Do you think she had
a change of heart?
Even if she didn't,
at least we finally have
the U.S. government
off our backs.
We won.
What...
Hey.
We won the hotel, yes,
but now...
We're on our own.
Yo, Steve-o.
Over here.
Drink up. We're celebrating.
What's there to celebrate?
We all just lost our jobs.
What, you thinkl'd just
leave my guys out
in the cold? Come on.
Okay. Sure, the hotel's
been shut down,
but there are still plenty more
of them out there,
out in the open.
You see,
the government's looking
for good, honest folks like us
to start following leads,
rounding them up
from the tip line. And it pays?
Real money this time,
plus benefits.
No more of that
subcontract bull.
Yeah! Let's round them up!
You know, Steve-o,
you're one of the good ones,
I've got your back,
don't you worry.
Round them up. Hey, that's
what we like to hear.
Oh, my God.
First of all,
this is kind of creepy.
Can we meet somewhere
with more lights next time?
You have what I asked for?
You'll find all the
stolen Ypsi Med files
on that thumb drive.
No copies were made.
Anyone put together what
these files actually contain?
Just a recurring word, "ZMT."
What is ZMT, by the way?
All in due time.
Patience is a virtue after all.
Thank you
for your service, Agent Abbas.
I never doubted you
for a second.
Welcome to the inner circle.
So, uh, hooking up is one thing;
Having keys is
a whole other step.
Okay, look,
I've just been getting.
Manny's stuff out of here
and watering her plants.
It's not like I'm keeping these
once she's back.
Yeah, I'll take that bet.
All right, so
what are we looking for?
Well...
This.
After striking out with
all the books at my place,
this is my last chance.
This box of Manny's books
that I left for Claudette.
Classics that she missed,
or that time travel
skipped her over, I guess.
Of course.
Time travel.
'Cause what is
the shortest distance
between two points,
traveling through
the fifth dimension...
Like A Wrinkle in Time.
Oh, my God, and there's
our code with a new number.
Manny used to be obsessed
with this book.
- He always identified with...
- Charles Wallace.
He would even call me Calvin
if I was too slow
in picking up whatever it was
he was trying to explain to me.
But there's not 1,269 pages
in this book.
Well, does the book
tell us anything?
About Manny, the codes, or...
What is it about?
I don't know. It's about...
family and about
overcoming your fears,
and always having faith
in one another. And that...
even if you
don't understand something,
or you don't seek it,
even if it's
right in front of you,
that doesn't mean
it doesn't exist. And, oh yeah,
it's about time travel.
Good. Let's just observe 48,
for the time being.
No need to bring her in
just yet.
How's the transition going?
All in order,
thanks to my signature.
Why did we grant them sanctuary?
Sitting ducks. They'll think
they kicked us out,
but... With the world at large
seeing them
more and more as a threat,
they'll eventually
round themselves up.
And we'll know exactly
where they are.
We finally have cover
to make that arrest.
Good. Make sure he tells us
what we want to know.
I will.
Police. Open up.
Do you think someone called
Claudette in to the tip line?
So help me,
if that's the case...
Jharrel Mateo? Yeah?
Hey, whoa. Hey!
Hey. What... Get off of him.
What the hell is going on?
There's got to be
some kind of mistake.
His warrant.
Theft of government property.
Keisha, you got to get Carla.
She'll know what to do.
You got to get me out of this.
Keisha! Someone
is setting me up.
Keisha! Get me out of this!
Captioning sponsored by CBS.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org