That's not even...
That's just not
how it happened.Keisha.
Our first night out in I can't
even remember, and you get us
kicked out with a dance-off.
Miss RiRi tells you to work,
you got to work.
Yeah. See? That's
exactly what...
Mm-hmm. You know I don't like it
when you sign in secret.
But the buns are fresh,
I can assure you.
Oh, so you coming for me now?
Don't start nothing
you can't finish.
Trust, little sis,
I'm-a finish it.
Come on. Uh.
Come on, baby.
Hey! Hey!
Keisha. Hey, Tarik.
I-I just came to drop this off
for the girls' tuition,
all right?
Does this mean you're not coming
to Sasha's recital tomorrow?
You know, work's been crazy
since this new 4,400 detail.
I got a lot
to catch up on, so...
Sure.
It's always work.
You know, the girls
really miss you.
You haven't been by in weeks.
Yeah, I know. I just...
Give them a hug for me, a'ight?
There's something else. Keisha.
I got a letter last week.
From him.
Who?
The man who killed Kenya.
He wants to meet with me.
And you.
From what it sounds like,
he's turned his life around
in prison.
For real. He wants
to make amends
and to apologize
to both of us. No way. No way.
No way. Tarik,
that man might have you fooled,
but I will never go
anywhere near him,
let alone hear him out, okay?
You think I don't know that? No, he took
everything from us!
And he's rotting in jail
where he belongs.
All right. Everyone,
I'd like to introduce
Bill Greene.
Bill is our new federal liaison
for the 4,400 Project.
He'll be coordinating Phase 2
of Project Reintegration.
Bill? Thank you, Agent Tanner.
After the success with Phase 1,
D.C. has decided
to move into Phase 2:
Provisional release.
I know, I know. I know
that there are still questions
about the 4,400.
Everything from elaborate hoax
to-to alien activity
to time travel
is still being investigated.
But after everything
that happened
in that leaked video,
the public is asking
for their release.
Transitioning them
from these government facilities
and into the world
is the best option for everyone,
especially them.
In the coming weeks,
we will be vetting housing
both for people that want
to live with family members
and those who want to live
on their own.
Participants chosen
for Phase 2 will be able
to come and go from the hotel
with some rules, as
outlined in your briefing.
Basics
like curfew
until permanent housing
is approved,
regular check-ins
and health screenings
will be mandatory
for all participants.
Great. So they're on parole.
No. No, no,
these are temporary measures
till all of the 4,400
are released for good.
Unless
anyone here sees a reason
why they shouldn't be?
Good.
Now, remember, these returnees,
above all else, are people.
They should be given
the same dignity
and respect
that we all deserve.
Agent Abbas will be running
our tech courses
as well as supplying
our outgoing 4,400 with phones.
If you have any questions,
please reach out either
to myself or to Agent Tanner.
Let's get to work.
Soraya.
Looks like
we'll be vetting
housing options.
I guess I just didn't realize
they'd be free so soon.
Hey, you.
What're you looking at?
Jharrel is taking me
to visit apartments today.Oh.
This one
is near a park, and this one
has a swimming pool.
You're welcome.
For leaking the video I made
on Soraya's computer.
What, you thought the government
was setting you up
with a pool out of the goodness
of their heart? No.
This is CYA for making them
look bad in public. I'm just waiting
for the other shoe to drop.
I mean, when has the government
done anything for us folk
without a catch? Well, I'm glad
you're getting out.
Some of us aren't old enough
to live on our own yet,
so we're still prisoners.
Especially when people like that
are still in here
with the rest of us.
Okay, like, I get the kid's
mad his little girlfriend
isn't back yet, but damn.
If the video's
getting people out,
that should be worth something,
right?
My apologies, Mrs. Murray.
No, not at all.
It's my bad.
Sleeping well, I presume?
I seem to be the only member
of the insomniacs club
this past week.
Right, yeah.
No, uh, it's, um...
I'm not avoiding you
since our-our...
Nor am I you.
I have a surprise
for you.
If you would be so kind
as to accompany me?
Where?
Where does it lead?
Let me show you.
May I?
I presume Miss Mildred worked
her magic on yours, as well?
They'll never know we're gone.
Mariah Kaminski
fakes right.
She flicks to the shoulder.
Bam! Flunge to the head.
Oh, enjoy the silver, Tessa.
This calls for a celebration.
Yes. Whatever you want, kiddo.
Listen, we discussed this.
We are considering it. Come on,
Dad. I mean, I get it's awkward,
but Shanice staying here
with us?
It feels
like we could actually be
a family. Allof us.
I mean, I...
I just want to get to know her.
I understand that, Ry, but...
The house is being vetted today.
I mean, do you really want her
locked up in a hotel room
when we have
a perfectly good room here?
If it's something
you really want, sweetheart,
we'll make it happen.
Thank you, Mom.
Hello?
Yeah, hi.
Video?
What video?
This is crazy.
I never thought I'd actually
use a prohibition tunnel.
Feel like Nancy Drew.
Okay, first stop, the library.
Wait, should we be doing this?
We're about to be released.
If we get caught,
they could retaliate.
Youare about to be released.
I don't know
when my time will come.
I haven't heard anything yet.
You promised to show me Detroit.
And before you go
back to your family,
I want to spend one last day
with you.
Well, a promise is a promise.
Look, I just think
something seemed off.
Well, you should speak with her.Morning.
My name is Miguel,
the new on-site doctor.
Lovely to meet you both.
Nice to meet you,
Miguel. We were try... I'm vetting
family housing options
for Shanice Murray.
Yes. Mrs. Murray has been
cleared for release.
And I am with Claudette
Williams today.
Uh, maybe we should switch.
You can do the walkthrough
at the Kaminskis',
and I can take Claudette. Oh, hard pass.
What, vetting Logan's
house so that his ex-wife
can stay with him
and his current wife?
Yeah, I want
no part of that drama.
All right, here we go.
Both screened and cleared.
Anything else I can do for you?
That's about it. Are you sure
they're cleared?
Uh, has anyone
come to your office
with anything... weird?
Do they need any more shots?
Blood samples?
Like I said, they're good to go.
Thank you, Miguel.
Yo, what is your deal?
First, you were weird at
the staff meeting earlier,
then whatever the hell
that was with Miguel.
Keisha, we're partners.
All right? You can talk to me.
I'm concerned, okay?
What if the medics
miss something?
What if we miss something?
You have to admit,
weird stuff
follows these people around. Yeah,
because the government is
pitting them against everyone. Oh,
did the government put us to
sleep on Belle Isle that night?
We never even got
to hear what Soraya found.
And last week on my outing
with Shanice and Claudette,
I saw...
It just...
It makes me nervous, okay?
I-I don't want anyone
to get hurt.
Okay, and here I thought
you were finally coming around
on "these people."
Why are you so quick
to believe the worst in them?
I guess you can't take
that cop hat off, can you?
Look, screw you, Jharrel.
You're not gonna paint me
as some kind of monster
for trying to keep the public
safe, for doing my job.
What, finding excuses
to keep people locked up?
Wow.
What a great job.
My, my, my. This city
sure is something.
Oh, I can't believe
how good this feels.
You want to look up directions
to our next stop?
I know
you didn't just ask me that.
It's how we get around in 2021.
Well, I barely trust paper maps.
I'm sure as hell not gonna trust
some gadget I don't understand.
All right, fair enough.
I miss driving.
Wind in my hair.
My own little pocket of freedom.
Where were you?
When you were taken?
Does that mean you believe
we were taken
from different places and times?
'Cause shoe on the other foot,
I don't know if I'd believe us.
Well, believing y'all means...
my missing brother Manny
could still be out there.
You know, it means that I
don't have to give up hope.
'Cause if you can go
from the 1950s to now,
anything's possible.
And, unlike
some of my colleagues,
I believe y'all when you say
that you have nothing to hide.
You know? You're not
some threat to the public.
I just want to give
you all the chance
to show the world
that you can be trusted.
You ready?
Ready for what?
Uh, there is a gas station
up the road.
I'm gonna fill it up,
and you can get
behind the wheel and...
You're gonna let me
drive your car?
Yeah.
I told you, I trust you.
I can't believe how much
it's changed in 16 years.
Were there canines pushed
in strollers 16 years ago,
or is this a more
recent development?
Oh. Cars.
How do they not crash
into each other at such speeds?
Oh. The lighted beacons.
Do they communicate
with the cars? Wait, Andre.
Hey, watch it.
Come on. Got a lot to see.
Really appreciate you taking the
lead on these tech tutorials.
Sure. Happy to help.
Soraya here will get you set up
with everything you need, ma'am.
Mine doesn't have
an "on" button.
Uh, so,
just like we did in class,
you just toggle
your phone a bit,
and then the home
screen will pop up.
My God.
How does it know how to do that?
Gyroscope?
Or maybe the light sensor?
Both, actually.
Thank you.
I didn't know you were back.
I'm sorry about the video,
but, you know,
desperate times and all that,
so...
Speaking of, um,
I need your help.
So, me and Andre
are trying to crack
this COBOL code.
Do you maybe have, like,
a program that we could...
Are you kidding me right now?
Do you have any idea
what I've been through?
I trusted you, and
you betrayed me.
Plus, I've seen enough
of your fake apologies on TV
to know one when I see it.
I'm sorry, fake?
No, I was trying to... I should go.
Before you get us both
into more trouble.
My husband had
a 1951 Oldsmobile 88.
Mm, how that machine could run.
Yeah, what did you do back then?
In Mississippi?
I was an activist.
A photographer.
Organizing sit-ins and
getting the word out.
My husband may have been
the face of the movement,
but my photos
are what made the papers.
You know what? Now the 4,400
are the ones in the papers.
I'd just as well prefer
to stay behind the camera.
Yeah, but you...
You traveled through time.
That's got to be...
It must be wild.
I'm here now. Just trying
to make the most of it.
Yeah?
No, I can't right now.
Because I have a job.
All right, fine. I'll be there.
Hey, I'm sorry. Can you
pull over at the next bend?
I got to take you back
to the hotel.
What? Now?
We aren't due back
until at least 3:00.
I wa... I was hoping we
could grab some lunch out.
That hotel food is criminal.
Okay, how about this?
We can get lunch, but...
you got to come
with me somewhere first.
Where we going?
Hey, Hayden. Can I come in?
Any news on Mildred?
Or Noah?
Isn't it your job
to get them back?
I will make a call
to Ypsi Med myself.
See if I can get any updates.
But my job is a parole officer.
I help people who are
newly free stay free
by making sure they're equipped
to deal with the outside world.
I have that same
protectiveness for you.
For all the 4,400.
Which is why I need to make
sure there are no surprises...
before I'm out there
vouching for everyone.
Because I was with Claudette
at Mrs. Grover's,
and I saw something.
But I protected her.
I did my job.
And I can only do
that job if the people
I'm trying to help are
honest with me, so, Hayden,
please... if there's anything
I need to know before we go
out into the real world,
I need you to tell me.
I don't like to lie.
And I don't like being lied to.
What is this?
Welcome.
Pray tell, what country does
this flag belong to?
Uh, it's the Pride flag.
It, uh, represents
the LGBTQIA+ community.
Um, it's all about inclusion.
This is a place where
everyone can celebrate
exactly who they are
and who they love,
and show that love
to the world, proudly.
We should stay.
I've never been to Pride,
and we could celebrate
our first one together.
How is this even possible?
This is just like
my and Cynthia's little corner
of Harlem, but...
all out in the open.
It's marvelous.
Yeah... marvelous.
We don't have to stay
if you feel uncomfortable.
No. That's not...
It's not Pride or anyone here.
I'm not about to judge
who or how anyone loves.
Then what's wrong?
Andre, I was married
three weeks ago.
He's still...
out there.
And I'm...
You and I are...
I'm not asking for anything.
All I want is for us to have
one last day out on the town.
No matter what happens tomorrow.
She'll have her own bedroom,
her own bathroom.
Um, just across the hall
from Mariah.
Our room is at the other end,
which is... good.
The neighborhood's very safe.
I run every morning,
rain or shine.
Um, Mariah's
really looking forward to
spending more time with her mom.
Mother... Shanice.
I'm sorry,
I feel like I'm bungling this.
No, you're, you're doing great.
It's not just this...
Last time I saw you,
you were on my porch saying.
Shanice is
a national security threat,
then Mariah gets called
in for questioning...
Well, like I said,
she's a minor, so...
And now I'm giving you
a tour in hopes
my husband's
first wife moves in?
I know...
Shanice is
Mariah's biological mother.
But...
is it safe to have her here?
In our home?
Is that a terrible thing to ask?
No, no, it's not.
You know, our medics and
officials
have cleared everyone
for release.
But everything's a risk, right?
I guess you have to decide
if not taking the risk
is worth the regret.
Let's go see the backyard.
What are you... Listen.
Listen, act
like we're buying some coffee.
Um, buying coffee, what?
Shh! Shh! Let me know
if you ladies need any help.
Take your time.
My office got a tip
that this place is gonna be
available for lease soon.
Like, a matter of days, soon.
Okay, does he know that?
Picture it... down the street
from the library,
excellent foot traffic,
enough space
for the banquette by the door,
like you always wanted.
But you're gonna
have to act fast
because this place will get
snatched up quick.
But I do think I can get it
for a steal.
Oh, Ken, be real...
I can't just empty my savings
for something so risky.
Look, I got to think
about you, the girls...
You don't.
Nobody asked you to do all that.
Tarik and I can handle it
on our own just fine.
Come on, we both know
money has been tight for you.
Plus...
Say it.
We both know you and Tarik
haven't always been
the most stable couple.
Mm-hmm, okay, see,
you always do this.
This isn't about me
or the girls or Tarik.
This is about you not wanting
to take a risk
to go after what you want.
And I'm not gonna let you use
my family as an excuse.
If you're too much of a coward
to go after what you want, fine.
But that's on you.
Kenya... Kenya? Uh-uh, uh-uh!
Look, I'm sorry about that.
Landlord's raising the rent
on this place, so...
got to let it go.
But, um, I don't like
people snooping around here
when I'm gone,
so whenever somebody wants
to see the place, I...
But never mind.
This is Manny's apartment,
isn't it?
Yeah, for the next 16 days,
yeah.
Yeah, he's been gone for a
year, but I can't let it go.
Not when...
When he could
still be out there?
Yeah, I know
it must seem crazy...
Crazier than traveling
through time and space?
Okay, you got me on that.
I never had a place of my own.
I went from my parent's house
to my husband's house,
to... well, the Bois Blanc.
The only time I had for myself
was one weekend a month.
Uh, my husband would meet
with the southern leaders
of the movement in Georgia.
And the second I heard that 88
rumble out of the driveway...
that's when me and my 33s
came out to play, honey.
I'd cook cornbread
in my mama's skillet, and...
listen to sinful men
croon to me on my record player.
I lived for those weekends.
No wonder you lot are obsessed
with those things.
You know what?
There is a meat and three place
delivers here...
best cornbread in town.
All right.
When they didn't do it
with the flag... Yes!
Shanice?
Logan, uh...
We were just... uh...
Andre Davis.
And you must be Mr. Kaminski.
And Miss Mariah.
I've heard so much
about you both.
Check out a lot of clubs, Andre?
Pleasure to meet you both.
We just stumbled
across a Pride party.
You know, it doesn't... matter.
I knew you were cool, but...
I mean, a jailbreak
to hit up Pride? Nice.
Okay, but why are you here?
Are you okay?
What happened?
I'm fine,
they just had a few questions
about the viral video
I sent out, but...
Wait, you sent that video?
Do you haveany idea
how much trouble
you could've gotten in?
I'm a minor.
And I only shared a video
that was sent to me...
That's not a crime.
That's just... the Internet.
Okay, will you give us
a second, Ry?
Fine.
Listen.
They brought Mariah in
for questioning
about this-this
whole video thing.
DHS is questioning mydaughter.
And you're just gonna move in?
With all of this
surrounding you?
I mean, God knows
what'll happen with Mariah,
the more she's connected to you.
Whoa, Logan, I didn't
know... Exactly.
Come on, let's go.
All right, does anybody want
to do a lap before committing?
If you're looking for gentlemen,
there appear
to be some options
by the dart board.
Good lookin' out, C.
The bar. Mm-hmm.
So I know I'm only here
for my credit card.
But... thank you for the invite.
Not gonna lie, you looked
about as bad as I feel.
Which is... saying something.
Everything checked out today
at Logan's house.
Once I submit the approval, you
should be able to move right in.
Maybe even tomorrow.
I can't do it.
I mean, I was going to
for Mariah's sake,
but I can't live
with my husband and his wife.
Oh, yeah, well, that,
that is messy.
Totally messy!
How was his, um...?
Bridget seems...
sweet.
House is a little Chip
and Joanna for my taste,
but, uh...
I don't know,
it felt... like a home.
Good.
Yeah, that's good.
I know I should want him
to have moved on.
Like, a better person
would want him
to get remarried and...
maybe have more kids.
Live a happy life. I just...
I'm sorry, I didn't mean
to dump all that on you.
I-I've had a day myself.
I may not have come
from the past,
but it sure has
a way of sneaking in
when you least expect it,
you know?
Sanitation check!
If you have any contraband,
you better tell me now.
I-I-I don't.
Well, well, what's this? It's my chess set.
Looks like someone's got
sticky fingers.
I'm confiscating it.
What? No, no, it's not,
it's not stolen, please!
Another video comes out
with this place looking
anything less than clean and
orderly, we might lose our jobs.
You wouldn't want that, right?
To see
good working people fired?
But it's mine.
My-my friend gave it to me.
Well, your friend clearly stole
government property.
So either I take this now,
or you give me
the name of your friend.
Oh, "texpert."
I tried to catch up
with you earlier,
but you ran off pretty quickly.
Yeah, there's just
a lot going on here.
Sure, sure, but...
I mean, what happened?
Are you okay?
Uh... I'm fine.
Just... busy.
Right.
All right, well, I'll get
out of your hair, but...
Listen.
What did you want to tell
me before you left?
About the body cam footage
from Belle Isle?
Is it something to do
with Manny or...?
There's just
a lot going on here.
But no, it-it turns out
the tape was nothing...
It was just...
someone singing.
Singing?
Uh, maybe it had something
to do with the song itself or...
Or maybe it's the singer?
Look, whatever it is,
you're on your own.
I just had eight days
of brutal questioning
to think about it and...
my answer is
that it's just a song.
Anything past that,
I'm not your girl.
Oh, Soraya, I didn't...
I'm so sorry. I gotta go.
We have been given
a second chance!
Who else can say that?
We could do anything we want! Preach!
I'm gonna learn pottery.
Sure you are!
Uh, from the table
in the corner.
Well, look at that.
We're famous!
Freaks!
Excuse me?
Hey, he is not worth it.
I'm not worth it?
I saw your video online.
You and your little alien
lizard-people friends
better steer clear of this bar.
Or something bad's gonna happen.
I'm scared. Shakin' in my shoes.
That's right, bitch.
Who's the bitch now?
We need to get her some help!
No, I'm fine!
You were never here.
Okay, get back
to the hotel, now!
Hey, Soraya, um,
look, I want you
to know how sorry
I am for what happened to you.
If I knew you'd get taken away
like that, like... I guess
I just didn't think about
the bad things
that video could do.
Which is what I saw tonight.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
That means a lot.
Listen.
You know what it feels
like to be treated
like you've committed a
crime when you haven't.
I mean, yeah, of course.
I'm Muslim,
queer, a woman and work
for the U.S. government.
Being questioned is
being convicted
in the eyes of a lot of
the people around us already.
So when I was
dragged out of here
in front of my peers, basically
accused of treason...
it's fair to say
I don't feel
any more safe coming to work.
You should know...
the United States is a far more
frightening place
than it was six years ago
when you disappeared.
More divided.
Facts are gone.
Truth is debated.
And people who are
supposed to protect
people like you and...
and the 4,400...
You should be careful is all.
For what it's worth...
I'm on your side.
That's why I'm a queer Muslim
woman working in the government.
It is certainly not for the pay.
Thank you, Soraya.
For everything.
And, um...
not for nothing, but...
it took mad skills
to do what you did.
Couple more classes,
maybe I could hire you.
At least that way
I could fire you
next time you
screw up so royally.
Night.
Shanice?
I missed you at our...
Thanks, Logan.
I love you.
Tell me why.
No, make it make sense to me.
Why would you disgrace.
Kenya's memory by going to visit
the man that killed her?
You want to keep it down
before you wake your nieces up?
Now, I know this may be hard
for you to understand...
Oh, this is impossible
to understand.
I'm barely keeping it
together as it is!
I shouldn't have be standing
here, on your front porch,
begging you not to go visit
the man that murdered my sister!
What, we're supposed
to just forgive him?
I'm not asking you
to forgive him, Keisha.
I'm saying that I'm open
to talking with him
so he doesn't take
any more from me.
Like what he's taken from you.
What?
You used to smile.
You used to be fun.
You used to dance and bake
and sing off-key karaoke...
This was a mistake...
No, you never missed
a school play!
Not once.
I mean, God, you barely
see your nieces,
and it crushes them.
It's like you're not even
the same person.
Well, what about you, Tarik?
Hmm? 'Cause you haven't
changed a bit.
So what does that say about you?
You... Did you ever really love her?
I barely made it
through Kenya's death
in one piece.
The only thing
that got me through my grief
was forgiveness. I mean, God!
I could barely
look at you after I found...
What?
Come on, after what?
Tarik!
Kenya wasn't on the way home
from the library
the night she died.
She was coming
from the coffee shop.
She'd gone to take
some measurements
after store hours.
She knew you'd always
liked banquette
seating by the door.
So she wanted to get
a quote for the work.
She was planning on
surprising you. No.
I didn't know, I...
I was, I was going
to take her advice and,
and I was going to try for
my own shop, but after she...
I just, I couldn't... After Kenya died,
you devoted your life
to a system
that keeps people in boxes
and strips them
of their humanity
in the name of safety.
No, I'm trying to keep bad
people off the streets, you...
There is no such
thing as bad people!
Or good!
People are messy.
People make mistakes.
Choices they wish
they could take back.
You cut everyone out.
And it's eating away at you.
Bit by bit.
Kenya was my person.
And she died.
I'm worried, Keish.
That if you can't learn
to let someone in again...
Anyone...
Then you're living
in your own kind of prison.
And that's the last thing
Kenya would want for you.
Hey. Thanks for letting
me come over.
Course. Everything okay?
Please just let me say this
before I change my mind, okay?
I...
I'm sorry about this morning.
Between my sister's ex
and Kenya's killer wanting
to make amends, I...
I'm sorry.
It must be overwhelming. No,
"overwhelming" doesn't cut it.
When things got like this,
I always went to my sister.
A-And she was the only one
that could get
these feelings out,
and according to Tarik,
I need to let someone in
before I completely lose it,
so I...
I'm telling you.
Because I do trust you
even though you drive me crazy.
I'm honored.
All I ever wanted to do here
was my job.
Get to the truth.
Protect the people. But I...
Look, I have something
I need to tell you.
I saw Claudette...
heal herself.
Heal herself?
Yeah, she cut herself on some
glass at the bar, and it...
It was deep.
But then it just closed up
like nothing happened.
And I don't think this is
the first time, and...
I don't know what it means,
but I know it means something.
Maybe it's not about the song.
Maybe it's about the singer.
What?
Oh, yeah,
it's something Soraya said.
Listen, whatever's happening,
it isn't just happening
with Claudette.
Something
is going on with the 4,400.
Something beyond the scope
of our understanding.
And there's people out there who
already see them as a threat.
So, what do we do?
I thought we were going to
visit a potential apartment.
A place all your own.
Oh, my word.
Really?
Yeah.
The government is gonna pay
the new rental price,
and Manny's place
will go to someone
who will take care of it.
Win-win.
Thank you.
Listen,
there's something
I need to tell you.
I know.
Know what, exactly?
No.
I know.
You know about...
me.
Whoa, hey, it's okay.
All right? You can trust me. I knew
this was too good to be true.
It was Keisha, wasn't it?
Girl's got a big damn mouth.
You can trust her, too.
I promise.
We just want to help.
Hey.
Did you find out about Mildred?
Um, not yet.
But I'm working on it.
Hayden, I heard
about your chess set.
I'm sure that was
really scary for you.
I'm gonna report that guard.
Why?
That's what they do.
Yeah.
So...
How would you feel about
getting out of here?
Yeah, since Shanice
isn't leaving,
there's an open room
at Logan's house.
Mariah convinced him
not to let it go to waste.
Mariah did that? She did.
Logan signed off
to be your guardian
until we can find a next of kin.
But only if you agree.
You're important to me, Hayden.
So,
what do you think?
Yeah.
I'd like that.
We've tried the oatmeal bath,
but she won't stop scratching.
Yo, Keish.
Hey. Uh, listen,
I was wrong.
Okay, I may not be there yet,
but if you want to visit
that man in prison,
you should.
You sure you're okay with that?
Yeah, you should move on
however you want.
I just...
You know, I want you
to get what you need.
Y-You, too, Keish.
Thank you.
Hey, Jess.
You, uh, want to grab dinner?
No. I mean, maybe.
I, um...
I've been reassigned.
Wh... Reassigned? Where?
Ypsi Med.
Wait,
but if you aren't running things
at the hotel, then who is?
Good work.
Everything's
moving forward nicely.
But, Mr. Greene, what happens
now that the 4,400 are free?
They're not free.
They're just in a bigger cage.
We're happy to have you here.
I mean, you have
your own bathroom.
And the hot water
takes a minute,
but it gets there eventually.
Um, do you need anything else?
What else would I need?
I don't know. Uh, candy, soda.
Nuclear codes?
Sorry. Bad joke.
Um, so, what do you
want to do tomorrow?
We could go see a movie.
Oh, are you into sports?
I could teach you how to fence.
Get you battle-ready in no time.
I know what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna break Mildred out
of Ypsi Med.
Captioning sponsored by CBS.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org