No.
I want an attorney.
Uh, you can't hold me like this.
Oh, DHS can.
We got a tip
on those stolen files.
We can place you at Ypsi Med
a couple of weeks ago.
I don't know what files
you're talking about!
Did your brother ask you
to steal them?
Why would...
My brother has been
missing for a year.
You know that.
Manny's not missing.
We have him.
Wait, what-what?
Wait, you...
you have my brother?
Where-where have you
been keeping him?
Let me see him.
Let me talk to Manny.
I'd suggest you tell us what we
want to know about his research.
Jessica.
And your story better match his.
Let me talk to my brother. I'll be back
when you're ready
to start telling the truth.
Any word on Jharrel?
Nothing.
I tried calling all the contacts
I can think of, and no one
will give me a straight answer.
What can we do?
It's been two days.
Well, the warrant is legit.
DHS admits to having him
in their custody, and...
that's all I know.
All right, I'll, uh...
get some of this back
to the hotel.
I can't tell you how grateful
I am for all your help, Keisha.
We all are.
The climate's growing unsavory
for the 4,400
and our sympathizers.
Just take care
to watch your back out there.
You, too.
You okay here, solo?
Don't worry.
I'll be just fine.
I'm not gonna lie, these last
two days have been hard.
Everyone has questions
I don't have answers to.
Ji-Eun and a few others took
their chances outside and...
Even though we warned
them sanctuary status
only protects us
inside the hotel.
And now, now they're vulnerable
to anyone who
calls the tip line.
And they're at the
government's mercy.
Shanice, you are not responsible
for other people's choices.
And we're not under
the government's thumb.
Freedom is everything.
Yeah, I just wish
I could figure it out.
Rev and I did an inventory,
and the government took most
of our food and supplies.
People are
starting to panic.Uh...
things as they are might
not feel sustainable long-term,
but you are a tremendous leader.
I have faith in you.
Even if the day-to-day
is a bit more challenging,
we can and will fend
for ourselves.
Together.
I must admit,
it is a relief to just...
just be like this.
Without having to worry
about someone else's
memories suddenly hitting me
if I touch them.
Hey, Shanice.
No, wait... Mariah?
Wait, c-can you see me?
Yes. I mean, no.
Uh... Um, how-how do I turn this off?
This is clearly a bad time.
You called from earlier,
so I d...
I just thought I would...
You know what,
I'll call you back later.
Okay. Yeah.
Bye.
Do you think she saw us?
Most certainly she did.
Who's there?
Come on out now.
Don't be shy.
You scared me.
I'm sorry.
Come on, sweetheart.
Storm's brewing, and...
you're the most wanted woman
in the country right now.
Come on. It's time for both of
us to get on up out of here.
Look, just let me
see my brother.
See, that's not how this works.
You have to tell us what
you know about Manny's research
before we tell you anything.
Just tell me that he's safe.
He's being well taken care of.
We're treating him
the same as you.
If not better.
Of course,
he rejected the steak.
Said he's a vegetarian.
You look awful.
What up, though, little bro?
Oh, sure. Come on in.
Like we haven't been pretending
we don't exist to each other
for a hot minute.
What do you want, Jha?
You look awful. You okay?
It's just spring allergies.
I've always had 'em.
It's not a big deal.
Now, what do you want?
Some stuff you need to sign.
Finalize Dad's property probate.
Since you didn't bother
showing up to the funeral.
Is that why?
Oh, well, you would think
that's why I didn't go.
Once a juvenile delinquent,
always a juvenile delinquent,
right?
Hey.
Hey, okay, okay. Take it easy.
Bro, you are burning up.
Hey, you're really sick.
How are you gonna take
care of yourself?
Food? Medicine?
Let me...
let me stay here and help you.
Until you feel better.
You should eat.
No. No.
Don't, don't leave.
Look, just tell me
why you have him.
No.
Wait. No. Tell me
about my brother!
You've been mighty quiet.
Want me to fix you
a little something?
I don't think I'm old enough.
Oh, right.
I keep forgetting
they raised the drinking age.
Didn't you say you were
just at bartending school?
Oh, that belonged
to Jharrel's brother.
So, you want to talk about why
you threw that man out a window?
I just wanted to help everyone
else who was locked up with me.
But you didn't have a plan,
did you?
And I imagine,
with the government
and the whole world looking out
for your now
very recognizable face...
you've probably been scared
half to death.
I...
I don't know
where to go anymore.
What about the sanctuary?
Doesn't everyone hate me there?
I know they're scared of me.
Even if I can't...
you know, anymore.
What do you mean?
My powers are gone.
Rev took them away somehow when
I was in Bill Greene's office.
He-he took it away? I mean, I guess
it stopped me
from doing something
I'd probably really regret.
But, for once,
I felt like I was unstoppable.
And it just felt like
I had something
for the first time.
Hey, hey, hey.
Pick your head up.
There is power in that.
Right?
I have an idea.
Go on and get yourself
cleaned up
while I pop out for a sec.
Okay?
Hey.
Uh... you called with video.
There's no need
to hold it to your ear.
Mariah, about earlier...
I totally called it.
Mm, I'm not sure I...
I mean, I...
I know you and I
are still figuring out
who we are to each other, and...
your dad said
we could have a relationship.
But I'm...
I'm not ready to...
That's not what I wanted
to talk to you about.
So, things are not great here.
Someone mentioned crowdfunding?
I can help you set up
a FOMOFundMe page.
But the 4,400 is gonna need
a serious brand reboot
if you want to get the public
on board, so...
Sure.
Brand... reboot.
Okay.
Yeah, don't worry.
I mean, this-this'll be fun.
I am done playing games.
What were you
and your brother planning?!
What did he want you
to do for him?
Look, I'm not talking to
you without an attorney,
so you can stop asking me...
What was he working on?!
Ask him.
I mean, you do have him.
Don't you?
You know your brother's tattoos.
I'm trying to help you.
But if you don't give me
the information that I need,
I won't be able
to protect your brother.
What up, though?
Cops used tear gas
and pepper spray on folks
for peacefully protesting
Operation Legend.
That's what's up.
40 got arrested,
and I can't...
Whoa, whoa, hey.
You should still be resting up.
You really don't need
to be taking care of me anymore.
Don't Carla want you back home?
Carla is quarantining
with her own folks.
And she's worried
about you, too.
So take it easy on yourself.
For her sake,
even if you won't for me.
Hey, just because I can't smell
doesn't mean I want to stink.
It's hot up in here.
Plus, my brain isn't broken.
I can still fix things.
Covered up your old tat?
Thought having
our dad's last name inked
was something meaningful to you.
Was. I don't want any link
to him on my body anymore.
Right,
because you still blame Dad
for all your issues.
You know that man... That man
was a ghost to me
long before he died.
You know, I got that tat hoping
that it'd make him
proud for once,
seeing as how he told me
on the regular that I'd
never amount to anything.
No, but of course you knew that.
You bought into it.
Come on, you were angry.
All the time.
All right, if you weren't
getting busted for stealing,
it was for tagging.
Now you went and did whatever
got you that ankle monitor. What I did
was take a private sector job.
The Feds who had been
begging me to work for them
retaliated by claiming
that I stole from them,
fabricated charges to try
to force me to work for them.
This is their version
of a noncompete clause,
so I can't work
for anybody else.
So, what did, um...
you know, what'd they
want you to work on?
I mean...
what is it that you actually do?
It's hard to explain.
Seems like a hassle.
Why'd you turn 'em down?
I don't cave to bullies.
Not Dad.
Not the government.
I do what I think is right.
But I can't change
the way you see me, can I?
I'm sorry to just text you
out of the blue like that. I...
No, it's fine.
Glad you did.
I'm worried.
You haven't heard from him?
Nothing.
I'm sorry. I...
wish I could help.
Actually, I think you can.
What's the deal?
Well, Jharrel thought this
might be the key
to the clock code
you said we should look for.
It was in Manny's apartment.
But I don't know
what I'm looking for.
Can you...
break the code?
Figure out what Manny's
message to Jharrel was?
I mean,
who better to ask
for code-breaking help
than the world's
greatest texpert?
Texpert is on it.
Thanks.
I...
got to get this over
to the hotel.
I hope they're doing okay
in there.
It's so kind of you
to be bringing all of this in.
Having some hot food will
brighten everyone's spirits.
Of course.
A lot of people actually seem
to want to help the 4,400.
But, uh...
Hopefully all the others
will leave us in peace.
We're not hurting anyone.
No, it's not about the
reality of who you all are.
Some narrative that exists
out there of prejudice
against "your kind."
What in the...
No, come on.
Come on.
There's no power.
I think we're stuck.
Everyone else out there
has power.
This isn't the storm.
It's the government.
They killed the lights.
Everyone, head back up
to your rooms in pairs.
Let's ride out the storm.
Rev and I are-are responsible
for making this
sanctuary happen.
And everyone is looking
to me for answers.
And now I have to figure out
how we're gonna pay
for utilities?
We focus on getting
through the night.
I will gather supplies
from my office.
No one's ever given me
a makeover before.
Imagine you never been wanted
by the FBI before either.
Let's get started, shall we?
Hot mama.
Now, I am no professional.
So I can give you
a bob or a bob.
Just got to...
untangle this
bird's nest first...
No!
Don't touch me!
I'm just trying to
help you blend in.
You want to stop running,
this is what it takes.
You don't know what it takes.
All right, then.
Talk to me about it.
You're allowed your anger.
That's all right.
Is it because of
the Bill Greene thing?
And your time at Ypsi Med?
I... hate them.
They tried to take advantage
of my powers,
advantage of me.
I hate everything that happened
after the green light!
And... and everything before.
Just...
You might think
I don't understand
the pain of your past catching
up with your present, but I do.
I think it's time I showed
you something, Mildred.
They got what was
coming to them.
The Bois Blanc is
now without power.
Have you cracked
the book's cipher?
Hey!
Calling your bluff!
You don't have Manny.
Nah, you keep asking me about
him, what he's working on.
'Cause you don't
even know where he is!
You're trying to find him,
aren't you?
Where the hell is Manny?
All we know is
that an agent swears
she ID'd him in
Detroit last week,
and DARPA's been wanting to
find him since he disappeared.
Let me talk to him.
Hey!
Still waiting on that attorney!
I think I might know
how to break him for you.
Damn it, no...
no service.
Hey, but maybe I
can, uh, climb up,
see if there's an escape hatch.
If you hold the cart...
Hey.
Hey, you okay? I don't...
don't like small spaces, is all.
What if... what if
they don't find us?
Feels... Hey. Hey, whoa.
Feels like I can't breathe.Whoa. It's okay,
it's okay.
Look, take this off. We
won't be in here for too long.
All right?
Put your head down
and close your eyes.
Can you do that for me?
All right, we gonna breathe in.
Hold it.
Breathe out.
Good. Good, good. Okay.
One more time. Breathe in.
Out.
Thank you. I...
I'm sorry. I've...
never been able to handle...
No, it's all right.
I've had my share
of panic attacks.
Was hit with 'em for years
after my sister died.
Only good thing
that came from my ex
is she taught me how to...
breathe through the
panic until it was over.
She?
Yeah.
She.
So... you're...
you're gay.
Dude, chill! It's me, Logan.
You want to put down
the deadly weapon? Geez.
Sorry, I-I didn't mean
to give you a scare.
I would've come through the
front, but there's a crazy crowd
out there. Our detractors are quite
the impediment.
But, uh,
why have you come?
I heard about the outage
from Mariah.
Figured I'd bring some supplies.
I got tons of camping gear.
And this piece
of machinery?
Oh, the generator?
Won't power the whole hotel,
but I figured
it'd come in handy.
You know, hold over the kitchen,
the refrigerator a few days.
Indeed.
How thoughtful, Logan.
But I must continue
to sort through these.
Y-You know, we've, uh,
we've come a long way
since candles.
One thing I'd learned
in the war...
Hard times have a way
of lingering.
So, while these items
aren't as excitingly modern,
they'll last longer
than "a few days."
Sure.
Right, well,
I'm gonna go, uh, check for
circuits for the generator.
See if anyone needs help.
Tell me
that she has something over you.
Just doing my job.
Really?
'Cause I thought
we were friends, Soraya.
After everything
that we went through.
Now you feel like talking?
That doesn't belong to you.
Where did you get it?
All you have to do is tell us
where your brother is, Jharrel.
It's not rocket science.
It's like I don't even know you.
Then you haven't been
paying attention.
Jha, pay attention.
Tostones with mojo sauce
is my favorite.
How are you supposed
to make them for Carla
if you learn know how, huh?
You asked me to show you
how to make this.
It's all about timing.
I still can't smell or taste,
and you literally have one job:
Just mash the plantains
for a second fry. Yes, yes.
Sorry. Yes, one job:
Mash plantains.
Got a news alert.
Looks like vaccines are
right around the corner.
Hey, hey, you survived,
all right?
That's all that matters.
Look how far we've gotten.
Now I'm glad that we
can both get the shot.
You know, I never knew
that you could cook.
Well, I feel like you never got
a chance to know me, you know?
Back then.
Mm. What?
You gonna read me like one
of your social work clients?
Tell me that
"feelings aren't facts"?
No, I am just going to say
I'm sorry.
You know, I'm sorry I didn't
see you for you back then.
I do now.
Hey, uh, you okay?
Sorry to wake you up.
I know you said I should
conserve my battery,
but I said I'd check in, and...
I wanted to talk to you
about earlier.
What did you want to...
Andre and I are dating.
Is that, um...
weird for you?
No, not at all. Um...
I'm-I'm happy for you.
Yeah, I met him on our Ypsi Med
adventure and he had this
"everything old is new"
kind of vibe that I dug.
I kind of have a crush myself,
actually,
I just haven't really
mentioned it till now.
And you're telling me?
That's... that's awesome.
Let me guess.
Hayden?
Mildred.
Actually.
Yeah, I mean, she's fierce
and she's strong and she's...
she's amazing and...
Uh, is-is that weird for you?
Not at all.
Surprised, but...
I'm just grateful that you felt
comfortable enough
to share that with me.
I, um...
Shanice, I-I didn't know
how you were gonna fit
into my life before.
I mean, maybe this is who we can
be to each other, you know?
Mariah, I will always be here
to listen.
If-if you need.
Thanks.
And ditto.
Good night, Shanice.
You're making tear gas?
Like the feds used
at Kent State?
I'm not sure what
you're referring to,
but I assume they used
government-issue.
Mine's homemade.
I have no doubt
the government is tracking
our purchases.
Especially online.
Online?
The scariest word
in modern jargon.
This little thing is a passport
to everything and everyone.
It's how the
government tracks us
and how our enemies organize.
Uh, there's a page
called the 44orum,
and the hate that is on there,
the things people talk
about doing to us...
And tear gas is gonna stop them?
From organizing? No.
The tear gas is for when
they take action.
And believe you me, they will.
We have been scaring them
with our mere existence
before we ever fought back.
What you did gave the 4,400 hope
that fighting back
was even possible.
And now they see us as a threat.
So we're gonna be ready
to defend ourselves.
I've been learning
a lot about
the state of things in 2021.
You weren't really
at bartending school, were you?
And instead of disguising you
with a new look,
I got a better idea.
But we still gonna need to make
you over.
We have to trust each other in
the storm yet to come, Mildred.
Okay.
Do it.
You have a problem
with gay people?
I don't have a problem
with the sinner, just the sin.
But there are ways to change,
if one so chooses.
Okay, I'm-a to stop you
right there, Isaiah.
I am who I am.
I love who I love,
and I love how I love.
This is how I was made,
and I am proud of exactly
all of it.
Is that how everyone is now?
My son apparently seems
to be like you.
That's why you won't reach
out to him?
He's not the man
I thought he'd be.
You don't even know him.
I am a man of God.
A man of faith.
You can't just go against...
Please, Isaiah, it is 2021.
You got to get with it.
Plenty of faiths invite
all kinds of people now.
Lots of God-loving people
have realized
who the real sinners are:
It's those that hate,
not those who love
for the sake of love
without the conditions
based off some old book.
I don't hate.
Oh, but prejudice is hate.
Just call it what it is.
I heard the same kind of crap
from people just like you
growing up, and I...
I'd hoped that you were
different.
But, hey, sometimes people
don't surprise you.
Then... why'd you help me?
Hello?
Hey.
Hey, we're in here.
Please, help us!
Hello? Is someone in there?
Yes, we've been trapped
in here. Please.
- Okay, sit tight.
- I'm gonna get you out, okay?
Thank God.
Buildings like this
have generators
specifically for the elevators.
But the technology failed.
Well, more likely
someone turned it off,
I'm guessing on purpose,
because the door to
the generator is locked tight.
Ah, another parting gift
our government friends left us.
So you, uh, you know
how to pick locks, huh?
As I said, I believe
I can open this door,
efficiently and with haste.
And you really learned
all this stuff in the war?
Like World War I?
The war to end all wars.
Instead, it was merely
but the first.
Full of needless
suffering and loss.
You know, I actually met Shanice
protesting one.
Oh, you know what?
I probably... I've got to have
one of Mariah's bobby pins
in my... I'm not picking the lock.
What?
Kindly back away.
What are you...
Geez.
We know your brother's
been sending you messages.
Tell me what he was trying
to tell you with this.
I don't know,
why don't you ask him?
Oh, wait, that's right.
You don't have him!
His code is in here
somewhere, J.
What's it saying? You got me.
What's it say? What's it saying, J?
I don't know, Soraya!
Then you haven't
been paying attention.
My brother is all
that I have thought about
for a year.
Because I haven't seen him
or spoken to him
since the day
that he went missing
or was taken or whatever.
All that I have thought about
is finding him.
Do I seem like a guy
who has found him?
The only thing that
I can confirm on record
is that this was
his favorite book.
And he doodled in this book like
he doodles in all of his books.
I do not know where he is
any more than you do.
You can keep me here
all you want,
but I cannot help you.
All right, we're done here.
You're free to go.
Thank you.
And thank God for that,
ladies and gentlegays.
I never meant to offend you.
Thank you,
for your help in there.
You asked before
why I helped you.
I know my Bible, too.
Judge not lest ye be judged.
Yes. Matthew 7.
I know it. Do you?
I won't tell the people who
follow you how you truly feel
about some of them.
They see you as their leader.
Wouldn't want to crush
their faith.
Thank you.
I appreciate your...
You can do that on your own.
But just this once,
though, I am gonna judge.
I am so happy
you weren't there to put
your son through that crap.
Knowing what I do about you,
even if you weren't taken
by that green light,
you would've vanished
from his life anyway.
So he better off without you.
Hey.
Oh, my God,
what happened to you?
Look, I will fill you in later,
I promise, but Keisha...
Manny is back.
Okay, how did Soraya
get this book to you
if you were being held
in custody?
No matter what it looks like,
just know that
she is on our side.
1, 2, 6, 9, 16.
Those are the numbers
from the drawings, right?
Okay.
First two digits: Page 12.
6 and 9 are 69 sentences in.
And 16 spaces
into that sentence is the phrase
"would turn white with fury."
Wood. White.
You translate that into French
and you get...
"Bois Blanc."
Okay, so you think
he's here, at the hotel?
Yes. Where?
This place is huge. I don't know.
That's where I'm stumped.
I think that I...
Wait, no, that...
This hour hand
wasn't here before.
What do you mean? When... I don't know,
But it's got to be
the final clue.
It's not even pointing
to a number, it's pointing
at the space between
the two and the six.
I don't get it.
I do.
That space is a number.
Yo, yo. What up, though,
little bro?
Come see, come see.
With the vaccines
rolling out soon,
coinciding nicely with
the end of my house arrest,
my juices are starting to flow.
Ready to get back to work.
They probably thought
you were gonna cave.
But you didn't.
I'm proud of you.
You asked me the other day
what it is
I actually do for work.
I thought it'd be easier
if I just showed you.
Now, what do you think
the pineapple, the buttercup,
the seashell and the pine
cone all have in common?
All things we found half-eaten
by Grandma Lisi's iguana?
Okay, well, I can't
actually deny that.
But they also share
the golden ratio.
A mathematical principle
that's also called
"nature's secret code."
Now, this 13th-century
mathematician Fibonacci,
he examined the distance
between numbers in a sequence.
And what he found was that
the space between our reality
exists as its own and
often holds ours together.
Are you following me so far?
Uh, yeah, sure.
So this golden ratio maintains
a delicate and invisible balance
that's found in
everything, from,
from hurricanes to dolphins
to DNA.
To, believe it or not,
time itself.
What I do is think about
what happens
if you alter that ratio.
If you fundamentally change
the space between spaces,
how might that affect...
well, the world as we know it.
Man.
People pay you
to think about this?
Not just think about it.
But as for now,
I'm gonna go get us
some tamales.
And when I get back, I want
to hear your take on all this.
I'm really starting to value
your view of the world.
I have to find the space
between spaces.
Okay? Between two
and six is four.
Between six and nine is three.
Between nine and 16 is seven...
Four, three, seven.
Room 437.
I mean, you think...
Is it possible
that Manny's there?
I can go with you and find out.
Uh, no.
If I'm right, it's probably
better if I go alone.
And if you're wrong?
Well, then, I definitely
want to be alone.
Thank you, Keish.
For believing in me.
And my brother.
For all of it.
Hey, Jharrel?
Use the stairs.
Well, I must admit...
your knowledge of generators
was quite impressive.
Well... I-I certainly understand
their value.
Yeah, well, we wouldn't have
been able to rescue them
if we couldn't get
into the room.
I mean, when you blew the lock
right off the door,
it was amazing, man.
I know.
We made a really
good team up there.
It was pretty cool
getting to know you.
Ah, I-I got to say,
I'm digging this bromance.
My, what a compliment, Logan.
And while I appreciate
your ingenuity
and, uh, enthusiasm,
quite frankly...
you're just not my type.
Oh, no, that's-that's
not what bromance...
I can see why she likes you.
I thought the generator
you turned on
was just for the elevators.
It is.
Someone must have turned
the power back on.
All right. Well, uh,
I should get out of here.
Hey.
This was pretty cool, Andre.
It worked. The FOMOFundMe page
Mariah set up is fully funded,
by a single donation.
Remarkable news.Yes.
A-And who might
our generous benefactor be?
Not who. What.
Some company, BHN.
They commented
on our fundraising page,
"In solidarity.
We are all 4,400."
And they just issued
a press release.
Apparently, they just bought
the Bois Blanc, too.
Uh, though I hate to ask,
who are they?
And what might this company's
vested interest in us be?
I'm asking myself
the same question.
Right now, they're saving us.
I'll take any win at the moment.
Well done, my dear.
Manny?
I don't know...
I don't, I don't understand,
Did I get it wrong?
You found me, Jha.
I'm all right.
And I'm sorry for everything.
What up, though, little bro?
Captioning sponsored by CBS.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org