Manny, what are you saying?
You're telling me
you're from 2062?
2064.
I spent two years in what
you'd consider the future.
I don't... That's...
What? I'm here
because things in the future
are bad, Jha.
It's 40 more years
of the rich getting richer
by taking resources
from everybody else.
I can't let us stay
on that course.
Okay, so what? Somehow
you make the future better
by killing Rev?
Not to mention all those
people in danger here today.
Yes. Because today
always happens.
It happens in every version
of the timeline.
Okay, so why don't you stop it?
If it wasn't this,
it'd be something else.
It has been something else,
over and over again
throughout history.
There is a rot in this country,
people who believe in white
supremacy above everything else.
The system we have now
is cruel to its core.
The sooner we tear it down,
the sooner we can work
towards a better system
in its place.
We have to start now.
So people now have to die?
Manny, that can't be the way.
It's the only way.
Welcome, Manny Campos.
When am I?
The year 2062.
Still Detroit? Yes.
Although you might not
recognize it.
Michigan has been declared
a climate haven,
and the population has
exploded in the last decade.
It's been difficult.
It's all real.
We had a feeling
you'd catch on quickly.
I am Dr. Amber Campbell,
lead scientist
at our foundation.
What do you think of the place?
We have all of this
because of you.
I built this?
No. Sadly, in every version
of your future
that we observed, you died
before you could
complete the project.
But you did lay the groundwork.
My brother's waiting for me
in 2020.
He'll be worried.
We are of, course, sorry
to pull you out of your life,
but we think you'll agree
it's worthwhile.
But why this me? Why now?
Because 2020 Manny is as full
of hope and promise as ever,
of understanding the space
between spaces.
And who are you?
I head a team of scientists
dedicated to using
this technology in order
to better position
key people in time
in order to improve the
welfare of humanity today.
But we need your help
honing our vision.
The tech has a number
of limitations,
and our experiments
are falling short.
So far, they are not providing
the positive impact
the world desperately needs.
We believe you're the key
to our success.
Humanity needs you.
Will you help us
change the world?
I told you what I was
working on, Jha.
Breaking the fabric of time.
The people I was with,
they thought they could
make it work in other ways,
tried to make incremental,
agreeable change
that they could feel good about.
It doesn't work.
It never works.
Come on, we need
everyone's help.
Get those chairs over here,
stack them up.
I don't know how much longer
those ropes are gonna hold.
We're ready!
If they want a fight,
we'll give them a fight.
Right this way, sir.
I would like
some answers, please.
How about a cup of
tea while you wait?
Earl Grey?
I-I thought I was meeting
with the founder of BHN,
Ms. Sienna Stone?
What do you know about
Ms. Stone?
She works in technology,
and prides herself
on being against the government.
Which I applaud, but...
I'm not sure how much
substance there is
beneath the gleaming surface.
There's more to her
than meets the eye.
Please.
It's time to save
you God-fearing patriots
from these threats
to our way of life.
We are gonna protect
the innocent people
in this country.
We should be doing more.
Where are the authorities?
Why isn't Detroit PD
doing something?
We've been liaising
with the DPD the past few days.
They're monitoring the
situation, but they think
these outbursts of violence
so far are a few bad apples.
These folks,
they've-they've gotten
the appropriate permits
to camp and protest.
Come on. Really? DHS is monitoring,
too, all right?
We're all over this.
But look.
The 4,400 had asked to create
a sanctuary out of the hotel.
We have to make sure we don't
violate that in any way.
It's tricky.
So we do nothing.
Their methods may be crude,
and we certainly condemn them.
Of course.
But this 44orum group
will ultimately demonstrate
that the 4,400
need to be governed.
What does that mean? That the world
will see that the 4,400
can't be left
to their own devices.
They're going to need us
to step in.
And exactly how many casualties
will there be before then?
I thought
we were protecting people.
The questions you're asking
come with accountability.
Do you really want that?
Damn it, Jessica,
answer the phone.
I think we should get everyone
out through the tunnel
while Mildred holds the doors closed up here.
- No,
that's gonna be impossible. We
went through the tunnel first,
but the 44orumers were right
behind us. We had to cave it in.
What?
So we're trapped.
You can barricade
in the hotel rooms.
Okay.
Okay, everyone, find a room
to hide out in. Three or four
of you together. And barricade.
Okay? Quickly!
Let's get to the elevators!
Come on. You guys
get up to my room;
I'll be right behind you.
What was that?
Is that a battering ram?
I'm trying, but I can't...!
Okay, everyone
take cover. Now!
Find the reverend, their leader.
They'll all fall in line
once we have him.
Here's one.
No! Hayden!
Let him go! Stop!
Let go of me.
Come on, follow me.
Why are we listening
to this Millicent chick?
She's one of them.
We need her
in case we got trouble
getting in the hotel.
But she doesn't know
the real plan. We're gonna
round up those iguana-blooded
pieces of 44-filth
and bring them right back here
for extermination.
Yes. Including her.
Yes! Yeah!
We'll take this one
with the others.
You go get more.
Saw them go that way.
To the elevator. Quick.
What is going on?
Oh, my God, I'm so sorry we have
to be those absolute creepers.
I'm crawling out of my skin.
Okay, this is freaky,
but not as freaky
as when you were Jessica,
I guess. We have to get our people
out of here.
I'd rather take our chances
out there instead
of being trapped with them
in here. Let's get everyone
to the tunnel.
No. Manny's people
said it was blocked.
Blocked? No, we need that exit.
Yes, we do.
I saw that guy's memory.
They're planning to...
to take us somewhere and...
kill us. No, Lord.
They're in some
burnt-out warehouse somewhere.
That's their, like, sad
Mad Maxcosplay lair.
I've been there. It's not far.
Good. Y'all figure that out.
I'll head to the tunnel.
Even if I have to rip this body
to shreds,
I'll get it open for us.
And I'm gonna make sure
Logan and Hayden
are safe in my room.
Pray those monsters haven't
made it to this floor yet.
Oh, I'm ready to roll up
on their camp,
even if that means
having to be those dummies
for longer.
I can just...
I can just take Mildred,
and we can rain holy hell down
on all of them.
No, no,
we can't do anything rash. Rash?
No. After everything
they did to me,
to my friends, to my dad?
After what they did,
I want them to suffer.
I want them dead.
Yes, I know the feeling.
But anger
and violence will only backfire
on all of you.
And I know it's wrong,
but if you hurt these people,
you become the problem.
So, what do you want us to do?
I want you
to put that hood back on me
and get us both out
of this hotel.
You go back to their camp,
but just to keep watch, okay?
Make sure
nothing terrible happens
to the 4,400 they already have.
And where are you going?
I'm going to get backup.
I know
you can keep things handled
until I can bring back help.
Me? Alone? Yes.
You are as much a leader among
the 4,400 as anybody else.
Embrace your power.
Fine.
Look, those are my friends
down there, Manny.
Innocent people.
Do you understand?
I know, Jha.
And I'm sorry about that.
You're going to have to accept
that many of your friends
will not make it
through the day.
So you're murdering them?
Why?
Because I want to tear
down all the institutions
that maintain the status quo.
The many 4,400 who survive
today will be hailed as heroes,
but they'll also be vengeful
for the death of their comrades.
They'll use their
powers for change.
They'll activate a country that
needs something to believe in!
It shouldn't take people dying
to do that.
Thousands of people havedied.
Millions more are suffering.
This?
This is just the start.
I understand
what you want to do.
But I don't believe in it.
I just can't.
Jharrel, let me out of here!
I can't do that, bro.
I got to try and help
the people I care about
survive the day.
Jharrel!
Oh, thank God.
Shanice, come on. Are Logan
and Hayden...? Yeah, they're
already inside.
Come with me, and
I'll barricade us in.
Mildred, there's something
you should know.
They're gonna turn
against your sister.
What? No, she's one
of their leaders.
She's not... They're using her
to get inside.
They think she's just like...
well, us.
Look, I had to tell you
to give you the choice,
but you should stay with us.
She led them in here,
and she can fend for herself.
No, she can't. She doesn't even
know. She thinks that they're...
Look, it's my fault
that she trusts them,
and it's my fault that she's
put herself in danger.
Mildred, please, stay.
I can't just give up on her.
Please, be careful.
You, too.
Okay.
Get the chair.
Put it against the door. Grab this?
Yes, yes. All right.
Okay.
Oh, my God, Logan.
You're hurt.
It must have happened
during the scuffle or something.
Okay, we-we have to get you
to the hospital. No,
no, no,
you-you can't go out that door.
It's the only thing that's
keeping us safe right now,
keeping Hayden safe.
We can wait it out.
All right, kick the door in!
Mr. Kaminski, it-it looks bad.
Hey.
It's gonna be okay. All right?
Whoa! Can't stop
every bullet at once.
Take me to Millicent.
Oh, thank God. Renee.
You get that tunnel clear?
Best you get upstairs.
Help the helpless
to their rooms.
It looks fine. Aren't we
trying to get everyone out? Like I said,
you should help the others.
Uh, right.
All right, of course.
Claudette. Thank God.
The emergency lines
- are jammed.
- I'm running out to...
I think one of Manny's team...
My team...
Went rogue.
This right here is a bomb your
brother taught us to build.
Let's see.
And this looks like a map
showing where more of them
are planted around the hotel.
She didn't go rogue.
This is Manny's plan.
To trap the 44orumers in
here and bomb them to hell?
Yeah, along with the rest of us.
He claims he wants
to tear down everything
so the nation can rebuild.
I heard him talk
that way before,
but not about this.
We're supposed to be
defending ourselves.
I don't know. All right?
He claims that he came
from the future.
I don't know what to believe.
It's like
he's not even my brother.
Yeah, well, I got a
few words for him.
But first...
Now come on.
Look, I got you, Mr. Kaminski.
I don't know why
Andre's not picking up.
God, I hope he's okay.
It's Mariah. Oh.
Are you okay?
Is Dad okay? Are you safe?
We're-we're safe
for now. Uh,
we're trapped in the hotel at the moment.
- Give me your hand.
But, Mariah,
be-be careful.
They know your face, too,
from the Meet the 4,400 Event.
Where's Dad?
He's-he's not picking up.Hey.
Hey, Ri. Hey.
You look funny. Are you...
What? Feeling better
now that I see
that beautiful face?
You better believe it.
Oh, Dad.
Hey, Hayden.
How you hanging in there?
Really wish I had my
getaway driver right about now.
Hey, hey. It's too soon,
Hayden. Too soon.
Listen,
I-I've done
enough active shooter drills
at school. They-they might help.
Um, I'm sure you guys
have already done this,
but make sure
that your phones are on silent.
And they usually come in firing,
so make sure that no one's
in front of the door.
And, um, don't move
any of the wounded.
Are any of you hurt?
No. No.
And...
lastly,
we have to get off this phone.
Hey, I'm so proud of you, Ri.
I know.
We're gonna get out of this.
Okay, Mariah?
We-We'll see you soon.
I love you.
Love you, too. Love you.
Hey. Hey.
Ms. Stone apologizes
for the delay.
Something's come up
that requires
her immediate attention.
Well, then take me
back. All I asked for
is supplies to help
me with my research,
not some wild-goose chase.
May I?
Your ZMT levels
are about where we'd expect
for a 4,400.Wait.
This measures...
How did you know? That you're interested
in ZMT? Well,
yes.
And how do you possess
this technology
that exists nowhere in
the research I've done?
Sienna Stone.
I'm sure she'd be fascinated
to know your power.
It has manifested, hasn't it?
Still want to head back?
I'm glad you came. Sorry I
haven't been answering...
Why the hell isn't DHS
helping the 4,400?
This is domestic terrorism,
and you know damn well
law enforcement
would be all over this
if those people
looked more like me. I know. I know.
I just don't know what I can
do. Call in the National Guard.
There's protocol and red tape,
and technically,
Bill has to sign off on...
So we go over his head!
I'll reach out
to every contact I have at DPD,
and I'll give
anyone who needs it
a firsthand account from inside.
We have to do whatever we can,
Jess.
I...
You're right. We do.
I do.
What else did you hide from me?
I never would have been
party to planting bombs
that could kill innocent people.
Which is exactly
why I didn't tell you.
You were ready for a lot,
but you weren't prepared
to make that sacrifice.
Even though you know
this is how real change happens.
With a body count?
If there were 50 police murders
in a day,
if there was
a school shooting every day,
do you think
people would still
be able to look away?
Would people still think
that we could solve things
by making nice?
You're destroying a sanctuary,
Manny.
All right? People came here
to feel safe. They were never safe.
You know I agree on that, but
you're talking about making it
even less so. These
are my friends.
People I care about.
People that are only doing good.
But this is
how they do the most good.
To summarize our latest trial,
in which we sent 2,547 people
to 2021,
we are definitely
seeing improvements.
Poverty came down
by one eighth of a percent,
and the Latinx population
showed some political gains.
So, if we continue to augment
the number of returnees...
We've run the experiment
over 30 times.
We should have created
a whole new world by now,
but everything is the same.
Well, in our next trial,
we anticipate a 16% increase
in the possibility... It's not enough!
None of it is!
We sit here all day
in this pristine office,
acting as if the world outside
doesn't exist.
But it does.
The majority of the country
is nearly uninhabitable.
Are the so-called leaders
in this room
actually fighting
for fundamental change?
Or just enough
to maintain your status quo?
We are trying to help.
We are trying to give back
out of the goodness
of our hearts.
We are not doing nothing.
Except maybe weare the problem.
Because we keep doing
the bare minimum.
Just enough to say that we've
done something to help others
without actually hurting
ourselves.
Would actually change... No. No.
It's too drastic, and
the outcome is too uncertain.
Look...
Change takes time, Manny.
Well, that's just another way
of saying "wait your turn."
It will take
painful, harsh sacrifices
in order
for people to wake up and see
how bad things truly are.
What you're talking about
is a massacre.
And it's necessary.
I wish change could come
some other way.
But I know
in my heart...
You know in yours, too...
That it won't.
There has to be another way.
I thought you were
here to help us.
I amhelping!
I'm sad you can't see that.
Evacuate the premises.
Hey!
If you try anything,
I will make your sister suffer.
And the rest of you!
But I'm on your side.
I can talk to Bill Greene.
We don't care about Bill Greene.
The government can't save us.
We're taking our country back.
But...
Stop it, Millie. They're insane.
They're not going to listen
to you. Why can't you
see that? All of you, stop talking!
It's time to take care
of business,
make an example out of you.
Go! Up!
Millie! Please, stop! Take me!
- Let go of me!
The whole world's
gonna see this.
We got our first one
coming out now!
Bet she bleeds green.
Okay, LaDonna. You can do this.
Hey! Let go of me!
What are you doing?
I'm on your side!
Please!
Let go of me!
Don't do this!
Stop!
These racist,
fear-mongering scum can eat it.
Don't do this!
Hey. Hey!
- What's happening?
- Let me out of here!
- Come on, arm up!
- Let's get out there!
- What's going on?
- What is happening?
What the hell is that?
Where did you take my sister?
- Get out there,
see what's going on. I'm on your side.
Hey! What the hell's going on?
Don't try anything.
If you do, you're gonna
have to deal with them.
And we remember what you did
to us at the Bois Blanc.
Come on.
LaDonna's distracting them.
We can get
everyone else to safety.
If we work together, we can make
an unstoppable team,
don't you think?
I-I can't, Millie.
Please.
I'm sorry. No!
Wait!
Millie!
Manny left.
You okay? Yeah.
We have to stop him.
What are you thinking?
Your hand?
I've never tried
something so drastic.
There's 27 bones
in here, and-and...
I'd have to crush almost
every single one of them.
Wait. Just...
wait.
Look, since we don't know
what's gonna happen, I...
There's no time for
speeches, Jharrel.
Look, I-I know
you've come to care for me
in a far kinder way than the
man I left behind in 1958.
Okay, that's it.
We-we get out of this,
and I am taking
you Feather Bowling.
All right?
We're gonna do this right.
You already did
everything right.
Hey. Hey. Claudette.
Stay with me, okay?
All right, you can do this.
You are... Oh, come on.
You can tell me how
amazing I am later.
Stop.
Right there.
Okay, we have to tell everyone
that there are bombs
in the building. No, Jharrel. We have
to stop your brother
from setting them off.
Whoa! Hey! Hey! Hey! Oh!
You cut the tail off an iguana,
it grows back.
You cut off the head,
problem solved. Okay,
do you think you can...?
Decapitation?
No, I don't think so. You're the problem.
All of you
are the problem, and I'm
gonna protect my country.
Okay, hey, hey, hey,
I get how you feel.
Shut up.
I'm putting this beast down.
Manny, we found a way
to call in the National Guard,
and they're on their way.
Okay? We'll be safe soon.
Have you ever felt safe?
Which is why I say
more the merrier.
Let the 4,400 achieve
their true potential.
No, there's no way
that's the reason
the 4,400 were sent here.
Well,
at least we agree on that.
Manny, please step away.
Look, I understand
you are frustrated
by the process...
but we have 4,400 subjects
in trial. If you
insert yourself,
you'll compromise
the whole thing.
The trial was compromised
from inception.
Nothing ever changes!
Until now.
You will ruin everything
we've worked for.
No. No.
I'm finally gonna
make things right.
Manny! No!
Should we bring him
back to the bed? No.
Mariah said we shouldn't
move the wounded.
I'm sure help is on the way.
Hayden.
Bud.
You're very special to me,
you know that?
You got to take care of Mariah,
all right, bud?
Shanice.
No, stay... Stay-stay
with me, Logan.
Okay, please don't leave me.
I never wanted to leave you.
I love you.
Please.
You're not gonna kill me.
Leave Jharrel like
your sister's killer left you.
Heartbroken.
Hateful. Well,
clearly, you don't know me
or your brother at all.
And you don't know me.
Do it, dude.
They're crazy.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Are you okay? Yeah.
Keep the weapon.
We have no time to lose.
We have to get to the tunnel.
I'm gonna have to get
out of here, Hayden.
I have to find help.
He's still breathing.
Hayden?
Where's Manny?
Jharrel...
I'm so sorry.
Cops hit our camp.
Means they're on their way.
So it's time for us to kill
all the 'guanas we can hunt.
We have names.
And you all are trespassing.
One move,
and you kill yourselves.
This is the National Guard.
We're coming in.
Put down your weapons.
Can you believe they
let this place stay a sanctuary?
The video I posted
of their camp went viral.
They-they thought
they'd be glorified
for showing a 4,400 execution,
but now we're heroes
for shutting them down.
Hmm. Maybe the tide's turning?
Well, the thing about tides
is they turn back.
You still bummed about Millicent
throwing your sisterly kindness
in your face?
I don't really see it like that.
I wanted to save her. And I did.
I'm not her keeper,
like Caleb was.
Or Bill Greene.
Who reached out to me,
by the way.
He said he wants
to know how the government
can help us.
Wow. Very bold, Billy Boy.
Yeah.
I would not be surprised
if Millicent went back to him.
But also for us.
They may not have done this,
but they certainly
let it happen.
And what if they try to trigger
the conservatorships again?
Keep your enemies close.
I feel that.
Speaking of, I've-I've been
thinking about reaching out
to maybe-frenemy Sienna Stone
and BHN.
I don't know, I just have
a lot of ideas about
how we can rebuild
and rebrand this hotel.
Wow. You're gonna
take that on?
Well, I'm a leader, Millie.
Besides, some girl on a poster
once told me
to embrace my power.
Oh, me? Uh, yeah.
I tried to find you.
We were being debriefed
by DHS all night.
You-You're leaving?
I have to, Andre.
A-All of your texts and messages
flooded in after I left
that damn mansion.
I cannot apologize enough
for being absent
for yesterday's nightmares.
No, it... it's okay.
It's... None of it
was your fault, okay?
I need to get to Mariah.
Bridget is-is stranded
out of town,
and it-it's too much
for Mrs. Grover to deal with.
Uh, d-does she know about...?
Logan?
No.
And how am I gonna tell her?
I dragged them into this,
and now I'm gonna ruin
her life all over again.
We-we don't know
what the green light means.
Maybe it saves us in death.
Really, Andre? Has it saved us?
I-I don't think we know.
Did BHN or Sienna Stone
offer you anything
to help you figure it out?
Are we any closer
than where we were
when we landed on Belle Isle?
No. I suppose not.
Shanice, what can,
what can I do?
How-how can I help?
You have been my rock
through all of this
and y-you mean the world to me.
But I don't want to try to
figure this out anymore.
For me, the green lights
have ruined everything,
and I just need to-to get back
to-to...
I don't know. I-I...
I need to get away
from all of this.
From me?
No.
I mean, I-I don't know.
Welcome, Andre Davis.
In 40 years, there'll be
a time machine in here.
Ms. Stone. At last.
A pleasure to finally meet you,
Dr. Davis.
I thought the green lights
were our time machine.
You can think of those
as planes.
And our machine
like air traffic control.
Except that a stowaway
helped destroy the tower.
Manny.
That is exactly
why I brought you here.
You don't miss a thing.
Except for the reason
you have brought me here.
I would like to offer you a job.
With my resource and your brain,
we can have
a time machine in here years
before anyone thinks we can.
Humanity needs you.
Will you help us
change the world?
We can offer on-site housing,
limitless funding, so you can
dream as big as you want.
Thank you, Ms. Stone.
I d... I don't know what to say.
Uh, the housing
will be unnecessary.
And my colleagues
will be excited to learn
that I am formally on the path
to answering questions
we all have.
About that.
You accept my offer,
no one can know.
It's nothing sinister.
It's just...
We're dealing with time,
Dr. Davis.
We've learned that a butterfly
flapping its wings has
no effect on the future.
But 4,400 butterflies?
Monarchs who've migrated
through time?
Well,
it threatens
to destabilize everything.
You're asking me to lie
to those I care about.
No, I am asking to wait
until you know the truth.
Take the night.
I think when you return
to the Bois Blanc,
you'll see the merit
in my offer.
Glad you had a change of heart.
In truth, it wasn't
my heart that changed,
but everything else did.
Perhaps you knew it would.
You could only know about
that time machine
from the future
if you were from said future.
Did you keep me here yesterday
for a reason?
The attack on the hotel
was always
quite grim for you, Dr. Davis.
In all our trials.
What matters is you're here now.
Ready to get to work?
I don't even want
to hear it, okay?
I know it took me too long
to do the right thing,
but I know it was the right
thing because I got fired.
Jess.
The 4,400 were clearly
the victims in that situation,
and Bill just didn't care.
It's as if he wanted
to see what, like,
the 4,400's threshold was,
just to see
how much they could handle.
What? What happened?
Jharrel will never forgive me.
And I don't think
I can forgive myself.
Thanks.Yeah.
I spent a year coming here.
Seeing this place for all the
good things that my brother was,
when all along...
I'm so sorry, Jharrel.
That he's gone and he didn't
see fit to trust any of us.
That my last memory of him
was raving like a lunatic
about letting us die.
I mean,
thank God the National Guard
got there in time
to disarm those bombs.
If any of them had gone off...
I don't think he was a lunatic.
The sun's only come up once
since what's happened,
and the government's
already acting
like it's another crisis
averted.
Another date
that will ring the bell,
but bring about no real change.
Wait. How can you say that?
Public sentiment has changed.
Donations for the
4,400 are pouring in.
Yeah, guilt flows freely
into an open wound.
Just give it a few months.
Until the next hurricane.
Police shooting.
Pandemic.
See where the guilt heads then.
Jharrel.
I think Manny was right
about what's needed.
Uhp.
I leave for a half hour
and you invite a girl over?
What the hell happened
to my place?
Captioning sponsored by CBS.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org