So,
I know you've been in the dumps,
but I have the best
weekend planned.
I'm talking tacos,
pizza, Korean barbecue,
if I can convince Dad.
And... wait for it...
An all-weekend anime marathon.
Hayden,
you, uh... you there?
I'm sorry.
My mind was elsewhere.
I'm-I'm sure whatever
this Annie Mae does is sure
to be remarkable.
That's not...
Are you still thinking
of busting Mildred
out of that hospital?
Hayden, where... where'd you go?
I just had a... vision
of Mildred in pain.
Being treated worse
at this new facility
than anything
in the video you leaked.
Look, I-I know it sounds crazy.
No, it-it doesn't sound crazy.
I mean, visions from the
universe are no joke.
Some people just have,
like, a hella open
third eye.
So, if the universe says
Mildred's in trouble...
My world-famous Kaminski Cakes
are ready.
I know how much you
enjoyed 'em last time,
Hayden, so I doubled the batch.
I don't enjoy them.
I love them.
They make me feel like
this is home,
that I'm wanted.
Well, you most definitely
are, bud.
Okay, well, uh,
get 'em while they're hot.
And, uh, when you're done,
I'll drop you off
at the hotel
for your first check-in.
Are you sure
about saving Mildred?
Yes.
Without her, I...
I don't know
if I can be without her.
I'll help. Okay? Just
promise me
my dad will never find out.
And I can't believe the 4,400
have to be out of the hotel
by the end of the week.
After all that fuss
to keep them there,
now it's just... bye. Yeah.
With nothing but a stipend
and some housing
to help them adjust.
But they've left
Claudette alone.
It must mean they
don't know about her.
Or that we know about her.
Man.
No, I'm still kind of shook.
I mean, superpowers are real.
And Claudette wants us
to believe that it's just her.
Girl just wants to be left alone
to live her life.
She's currently nesting
pretty hard
in my brother's apartment,
but, well, I can't be mad
at her for that.
No.
Yo, you're not having
second thoughts, right?
About telling the government,
telling your girlfriend? No.
I don't trust
telling the government
anything at this point.
I mean, what would I say anyway?
A '50s housewife is Wolverine?
True.
You think she's the only one?
Between Shanice escaping,
our nap at Belle Isle,
and whatever went down
with Mildred, there's no way.
Man, if the government
had even an inkling
about half of this...
The 4,400 would be
locked back up.
Yeah, I want to help them,
but I don't know how.
I'll tell you what we do.
We ask them.
Trust me, I have
learned the hard way
that you can't fix people's
lives the way you want to.
You got to find out
what they need.
And the hard part is gonna be
getting them to talk to us.
Will you be
returning to Miami then?
My mom wants me to,
but some producers reached out.
Maybe I just go straight to L.A.
I don't know. What about you?
Back to New York?
Perhaps. Although I'm not sure
what's left for me there now.
And Shanice isn't there?
Well, that is... There isn't...
She and I aren't...
I need your help.
Oh, young Hayden.
How are things at the,
uh... the house?
At Shanice's husband's
and daughter's house?
What? It's not my
fault you're a messy,
time-travelling doctor who
lives for drama. It has been
two weeks since Noah and Mildred
were taken to Ypsi Med.
I want us to go get them out.
Look, I had a vision.
Of Mildred.
And a chartreuse door.
She was screaming and being
injected with something.
For some reason,
I keep seeing it again...
and again and again.
Look, we have to save her.
If we don't do it soon, I think
something terrible
is gonna happen to her.
Look, I have a plan,
but I need you both to do it.
I need your powers, LaDonna.
Oh, okay.
And your medical background,
Dr. Andre. What? Like, you leave
for a few days, and all of
a sudden, you're Danny Ocean?
LaDonna, the boy
misses his friends.
We understand
you're concerned, but
what you're suggesting
is a bit extreme.
We're all about to be released.
Now, this sort of action
could very well jeopardize that.
Especially when Jharrel
and Keisha know about.
Claudette's powers. You didn't
know about that, did you?
Look, she was barely able to
cover up for the rest of us, so,
now is not the time for people
to be putting a spotlight on us.
Mm. Besides, you said yourself,
sometimes your visions
aren't always complete.
They don't repeat, either.
Look, time is running out.
I can't just sit by
and do nothing.
I need her back.
That's Ruth's boy, right?
Yep.
My sister spawned a bit
of an odd duck,
if you catch my meaning.
And she's having to raise
the boy all on her own. Mm.
How you doing, boy?
You're being mighty rude
not saying anything
to your Uncle Otis.
Hello. Look at
your elders when
they're talking to you.
Now, if you're gonna keep
being disrespectful...
Then I'll discipline him.
Now, why don't you both
go get some drinks
so people can have an excuse
of why you're acting
a fool right now.
Come on, baby.
Hayden.
Hey.
Could you play a game
of chess with me, please?
Uh, I don't want to bother you,
but I really need this.
First, you're gonna sit down,
and you're gonna breathe.
Yeah.
Hey.
Now, despite how it looks,
I'm busy right now,
so I can't play with you.
So I need you to be
the sharp young man
that I know you are
and find a solution
for yourself.
Hey, hey.
Focus, Hayden.
You want to play chess.
But I can't play with you.
So how can you play without me?
I...
I could... I...
I could play against myself.
Oh, I knew you could do it.
Us Turners are amazing
problem solvers.
Mwah.
I can't lose her for good.
I won't.
- Amen, brothers and sisters.
- See you tomorrow.
Absolutely. Absolutely.
Thank you, brother,
I appreciate you.
Thank you so much for
these meetings, Reverend.
Before I found this group,
I was in a really dark place.
I thought God abandoned me.
Just remember, the Lord
doesn't leave us in darkness
without a little light.
A thing you know
better than most.
Thank you.
Have you seen Andre?
I have not.
But I do want to pick
your lawyer brain,
if you don't mind.
I'd like to find a way
to get the powers that be
to allow folks
to stay at the hotel.
What? Everyone
is finally getting out.
After all our pushing
and protesting,
we're gonna be free.
Well, many people,
myself included,
have nowhere to go.
This "freedom" might be
a salve for you,
but for myself and others,
it's poison.
Everyone is getting
placed in housing
and given a stipend.
You think everybody getting out
is the solution because
it works for your situation.
You'll be staying with
family, I presume?
Mrs. Grover
is like family to me.
And I'm pleased
that you have her.
This is a turbulent time
for us all.
And for some, being thrown
into housing they don't know
in a city they don't know,
in a world they don't know
is terrifying.
We've created a community here.
I'm sorry you can't see that.
They couldn't kick you out
if the hotel was a church.
Would it really work?
It's not a given,
but most still respect
the concept of sanctuary
that churches offer.
If the government
tried to kick us out, they'd
be drowning in lawsuits
from human rights groups
worldwide.
We just have to
get the word out.
Well... let's create ourselves
a sanctuary, then.
Technically,
you are the reason both
of them are at Ypsi Med.
Not on purpose, of course,
but, you know,
accident or not,
you do have to kind of
take responsibility for that.
Well, as far a responsibility
is concerned,
your video made us targets for
all sorts of ne'er-do-wells,
like that bar patron
who assaulted Claudette.
Touché.
It's just,
I've never seen Hayden
like that before, you know?
He's usually
all al-aloof and stuff.
But back there he looked really
ready to, like, square up.
Indeed. So what do we do, then?
'Cause he is really stubborn
and is not gonna let this go.
Trust him, I suppose.
The hotel is abuzz
with everyone getting out,
so our keepers
aren't watching us as usual.
And while lacking in context,
his visions come to pass
with unerring accuracy.
Great!
Now let's get on with it.
Stop doing that.
Oh, my God, you're gonna
give me so many stress lines.
You said you had a plan. I do.
We want to get Mildred and Noah
out of Ypsi Med,
hide them in here
till things quiet down.
First step:
Reconnaissance.
Starting with
one chartreuse door.
The technological advances
here are greater
than even I'd imagined.
Okay. I'm glad
you're enjoying everything.
Look, I know it's
taken a long time
to get you into a hospital.
And I cannot apologize
enough for that.
But we're here now, and while
you're doing your shadowing,
I'm gonna try and get some info
on Mildred and Noah for you.
It is appreciated.
It's been so long since we last
heard from either of them,
I'd begun to think our pleas
had fallen on deaf ears.
Name? Jharrel Mateo.
I have a shadowing appointment
for my friend right here.
I'll let the doctor know
he's here.
Oh, I had one more thing.
Could you get me the room info
so that I can visit Mildred Bell
and Noah Harris?
They're from the
Bois Blanc hotel.
The 4,400 are
in a different wing
and don't have visiting hours.
A different wing? Okay, but,
uh, I'm not a regular visitor.
I'm a caseworker. The 4,400?
Like I said, there are
no visiting hours.
Haven't been since they
took over the East Wing.
Go ahead and fill this out,
and here's a pass
for you and your friend.
Miguel?
Were you able to get everything?
Hayden, my boy, my lad,
my homie,
I got everything
and then some, okay?
First, we have nurse scrubs.
A size medium for one Dr. Andre.
Then we have patient scrubs
for you.
And then, there it is.
Thumb drives,
requested by LaDonna.
Why are thumb drives
shaped like food?
No? Okay, well, then we have
three two-way radios
and some earpieces.
And...
It's labradorite.
A gemstone well respected
for its ability
to banish fear and anxiety.
It can also boost
psychic abilities.
Try it on. Come on.
Why'd you get it?
'Cause I want to make sure
you make it out in one piece.
And we have an anime marathon
to do still, so...
Oh, um, my, um...
Shanice doesn't know
anything about this, does she?
No. Okay, good.
Do-do you want her to?
No, not at all.
I mean, she'd probably freak out
that this is really dangerous.
I know I'm just
the getaway driver...
And I'm all in... but,
I mean, I only have
my learner's permit.
Hayden, this is all
totally necessary. Right?
We have to get them out.
I know what they do
in places like that.
The guards here assaulted Noah.
The government stole him
away on my birthday.
They took Mildred, the
closest person to me, away.
Refused to let me know anything
about how she's doing.
And they destroyed
the chess set she gave me.
The set she made for me.
The only thing
I had left of her.
So, yes, this has to happen
because I need Mildred,
and I'm gonna bring her back.
Hayden, Hayden.
I'm so sorry.
It was a long day
visiting factories,
but I finally found
a distributor.
Your mom's baked goods
are gonna be sold
all through the Midwest.
I left a note
to your Aunt Marietta
explaining that you are
sensitive to certain textures.
She should have known better than
to make you noodles. It's fine.
No, it's not.
Sweetie, why didn't you
say anything to her?
I didn't want to.
Are you mad?
Never.
I love how careful
you are with your words,
but you need to advocate
for yourself.
Watch carefully, crumb cake.
I'm gonna show you something.
Solving a problem is
a lot like baking.
We start with what we want,
then look at what tools
and ingredients
we have at our disposal.
We put those together, and...
we get the thing we wanted.
Come here, come here.
There you go, baby.
Oh, how did
the reconnaissance go?
You two won't believe
the things I've seen.
In that device is a video
of Miguel... yes,
our doctor here
at the Bois Blanc...
Taking a 4,400 through
that chartreuse door.
And I caught him on video
as he put in the code
to open the door.
No way. You're, like,
totally the GOAT right now.
What the hell?
I taught you better than this.
Hayden, uh... Hayden, I'm sorry
to have jeopardized the mission.
We need to get behind that door.
Which means we need the code.
Wait, you saw him.
You saw him punch it in.
Yes, but I don't remember.
But Shanice can see
your memory; She can see it.
I don't think that's a good...
Isn't there any other way?
What the doctor's
trying to say is that
something happened between them
to make things
capital-A awkward.
Getting Mildred and Noah
out of that place
has to be more important than
whatever discomfort you have.
Please.
Imagine my surprise
when I heard you wanted to meet.
Even ordered you a drink.
I just wanted to try and build
a bridge between us.
One of more honest
communication.
Really?
Well, if we're being
honest, uh...
there are a group of people
at the hotel
who have created a church here.
They don't want to leave.
Why would anyone want to stay
at the hotel
after all that time wanting out?
Are...
are you... scared?
What are you getting at?
I know about the powers.
I saw Claudette heal herself
in this bar, and...
she admitted it to Jharrel.
What exactly did she say?
That it has nothing to do
with the 4,400,
and she was a secret superhero
in the '50s, and, I quote,
"Wonder Woman was Black first."
You must have been
pretty tipsy that night.
I don't know how
you let Claudette yank
your chain like that...
Shanice, I know what I saw.
You know I saw it, since it
happened at Mrs. Grover's, too.
Jharrel and I think
there are more of you
that have some kind of...
powers.
But we can't confirm that
unless you open up.
And if you don't open up,
we can't protect you.
We'll be fine.
I've tussled
with the government before.
Yeah, in 2005.
The 2021 government is
a whole different beast, okay?
You have no idea
what it's capable of.
Have fun hunting down
the other members of the...
Justice League.
Shanice.
Andre. Hi.
I thought you were avoiding me.
I've... just been busy.
I do have something
I need to talk to you about.
Hayden, LaDonna and myself
are planning on rescuing
Mildred and Noah from Ypsi Med.
Andre, no.
What will they do to you
if you get caught?
This is the time for us
to keep our heads down.
They already know
about Claudette.
And Keisha asked me directly
if more of us have powers.
She's not gonna let it go
until she finds something.
Well, the situation
isn't ideal,
but Hayden had a vision
of Mildred being held
and injected with something
in a separate wing of Ypsi Med.
It's likely Noah's there
as well.
Right now...
our whole plan rests
on you recovering a code
from my memory.
Can you help us?
Knowing how
we've been treated here,
I wouldn't be surprised
if some places are even worse.
Let's do this.
Do you see it?
No, I...
I see the hospital,
but it's all hazy.
Nothing really concrete.
Keep trying. I know it's there.
Look, I'm sorry.
This is new to me.
You can do this.
I believe in you.
I got it. I got the code.
Thanks, Logan.
I love you.
Andre,
I-I'm... Mrs. Murray...
the code, please.
Thank you for your help.
Shanice was a dead end.
Scratch that,
she was a brick wall.
Yeah, Andre really wasn't
in a talkative mood, either.
Look, clearly, if
we want them to open up,
we got to do something to prove
to them that we can help.
You know, actions speak louder
than words.
Hey, what about,
uh, Mildred and Noah?
If we got info on them, Hayden
might be open to talking to us.
And frankly, I want to know
what's happening with them, too.
Well, I got nothing.
Okay, Ypsi Med
is apparently a fortress,
with the 4,400
in some inaccessible wing
and absolutely
no visiting hours.
Well, I could go to Jessica,
see if she can give me any info.
You're gonna go to Ypsi Med?
You think that'll work?
You said actions speak louder
than words.
If we want them to trust us,
e'll have to do something bold. w.
Where are you taking him?
Um, he's...
one of them.
Okay.
This is no hospital.
There aren't even any cameras.
You said cameras are ubiquitous.
Well, yeah,
if you're not trying to be,
like, hella on the down-low.
No cameras means no evidence.
Okay, I'm gonna go
find Miguel's office.
I'm still in awe
of the illusion.
Cannot believe it is you.
I suppose this is where we part.
Good luck, LaDonna.
Do not forget to turn on
your earpieces.
We'll await your guidance
to find Mildred and Noah.
Medical staff must have
identification at all times.
We'll wait here for
Miss LaDonna's instructions.
Okay.
It's the same.
This place.
The walls.
The restraints.
Nothing's changed.
Hayden?
Hayden, please.
I need you to stay with me now.
I was in a place...
like Ypsi Med.
I was put there by relatives
after my mom died.
She was only supposed
to be gone a week.
Every night I went
to sleep there...
I heard the screams of others.
I tried not to scream.
I was already in pain...
from the tests.
The endless tests.
Hayden.
Hayden,
where are we?
Ypsi Med. Indeed.
You're not in the sanitorium.
The only reason
I'm not still there...
is because the green zap
saved me.
I won't argue with you.
This place is repugnant.
And that is why
we are here to save them.
Mildred and Noah.
Yes, Mildred and Noah.
Now, come back.
Hey, as the leader
of this mission,
they need you focused.
Okay, the map is acquired.
I repeat: The map is acquired.
You ready?
Guys?
Are you ready?
We're ready.
License and registration,
please.
Uh, can I ask why?
Your tags are expired.
I-I'm sorry.
Can I make a phone call?
- Hang a left.
- Copy.
Did you find any documentation
on that computer?
Yeah, I'm on it.
Better grab whatever I can.
After one too many Twitter
arguments, your girl knows
to always keep her receipts
at the ready.
We can't go this way.
Why? The coast is clear.
Not for long.
We need a new route.
Okay, if you turn around
and make that right,
that hallway
will take you around
to the far end
of Mildred's block.
It seems the restraints
are targeted.
Designed to neutralize
our abilities.
None of them should be here.
Okay,
once you make that turn,
it'll take you
right to Mildred's room.
There are two bullyboys
blocking our path.
What is going on?
Are you clear?
Doc, can you hear me?
E must have lost Miss LaDonna. W.
Hey.
I have an idea.
A birdcall.
That can't work.
Men were always surprised
how well it worked
in World War II.
Sometimes simple solutions
are best.
Birdlady acting up again.
Let's check it out.
Let me go. Let go of me.
Mildred.
Don't touch me! Let me go!
Hayden, Hayden.
You have to calm down.
We are not prepared
for a frontal assault.
I will tear them apart
myself if I have to.
Now let me go.
Stop right there.
Injection gun. Now.
Um, ma'am,
we need to escort number
48 to the operating room.
You're to, uh, go aid intake
on the new one
that just arrived.
They'll fill you in
on the details.
Oh, my God, go.
Now.
Let me go!
They're gone. They're gone.
Okay, so not a single thanks
for totally saving your lives?
Thank you, LaDonna.
LaDonna?
Hayden, is it really you? Yes.
And me. We're all here for you.
Hey, you're safe.
Okay, we're gonna go save Noah
and get out of here.
What the hell?
Mildred, what are you doing?
Showing him what
it's like to feel powerless.
Put him down.
The-the human body isn't
meant to take such trauma.
Sure it is.
He just has to push himself.
That's what they told us.
I'm sorry, but we had to stop
little Carrie here
before she killed him.
Did she? Um, kill him?
His ligaments must be shredded.
And his bones...
Shattered.
Okay, Andre,
we have to go... now.
But Noah. There's no time.
Come on! Go, go, go.
Um, where's our ride?
Could Miss Mariah
have abandoned the mission?
Hey.
Jess, I thought
we were gonna meet
in your office.
Hey... Keish.
Andre? What the
hell is going on?
Oh, my God, this is a nightmare.
LaDonna?
Just get in. We...
Please.
Just go.
A thank-you to Sister Shanice
for livestreaming our church
to the world.
Since we've arrived here,
we have had cause to worship.
Facing trials put forth
by hateful men
and doubting spirits,
we have conquered
more than most.
Bound by our unique
circumstances, we have all
learned to embrace
the illustrious spirit
of our fellows.
So I say to you all,
let unity be our doctrine
and love our discipline.
But I leave you
with one final message,
both to those 4,400
beyond these walls
and to the world at large.
We, the 4,400,
have been chosen by God.
Ferried by his divine splendor
across the seas of time...
I swear... for a cause
bigger than all of us.
Let this hotel be a refuge...
Nay, a home... for all 4,400
that wish to be united
with their brothers and sisters.
And let it be known
that I will provide
for every 4,400
that comes to me.
The government has no latitude
to expel you
from this sanctuary.
We have not just God
but the law on our side.
While those who seek
to harm and divide us
shall be met with the full force
of the strength
that God Almighty
has imparted onto us.
So, I haven't been to church
in a while,
but that seemed kind of ominous.
Well, Rev has a flair
for the dramatics.
Where's Keisha?
Well, believe it or not,
she's on her way to Ypsi Med
to check on Mildred and Noah.
All right, you got her?
Logan?
Mariah?
What is going on?
It's a long story. Andre,
did you know Mariah
was involved in this?
How could you?
Don't get mad at him.
Okay? All of this was my idea.
Now, say whatever you
have to say, but please
let us get Mildred inside.
Where's Noah?
There was no time.
Okay, well,
is Mildred gonna be okay?
I hope so.
Me, too. But, Hayden, how dare
you endanger Mariah like this?
Did you honestly think through
what could have happened?
She could have gotten arrested,
or worse.
Okay, that-that's enough.
We all know
what could have happened,
but it didn't.
Because Mariah,
at the first sight of trouble,
called me,
like I raised her to do.
And don't worry,
Mariah's gonna be
very grounded once I have
a long chat with her.
Oh, a chat? Well, how stern.
Shanice, stop it.
You do not get a say
in how I raise or
discipline Mariah.
Logan, it was dangerous.
Hayden is from the 1930s.
He doesn't know anything
about this world...
They could have gotten hurt.
You know, I've gotten to know
a courteous...
and kind...
and obviously very
loyal young man.
And while he's
also very grounded,
I'm proud to know
that Mariah has a friend
who's willing to do
the right thing
for those he cares about.
Now, go check on her.
I'll be waiting in the car.
It's so great
to finally meet you.
I had a blast getting to be
an almost-getaway driver.
I'm glad you had fun
while I suffered.
No, I-I'm so sorry. I...
I'm sorry, I didn't mean
to snap at you.
It was just really hard
in there.
Do you...
want to talk about it?
Not now.
Maybe never.
Anyways,
thank you.
Thanks for taking
care of Hayden.
Oh, I was... I was...
I wasn't really much of a help.
I mean,
I mean, Hayden is
the absolute badass here.
That's what I always tell him.
He is...
more than capable
of standing on his own.
Right?
Nice show you put on earlier.
I hope it served its purpose
to provide a sanctuary.
But it wasn't for show.
I mean what I say.
I'd rather break my back
than abandon my people.
I'm not interrupting anything,
am I?
You're not.
We were just finishing up.
How can we help, Mr. Greene?
I've been meaning to speak
with you since your sermon.
Seeing as you are
the man to know,
I figured we could talk
about how we
could best aid each other.
I'm all ears. Wonderful.
Wonderful. Please.
Ms. Murray.
Do you know
how many things I've done
that could blow back on me,
personally and professionally,
for trying to cover for you?
What were you thinking,
breaking into Ypsi Med?
You could have been caught.
We deserve an explanation
right now.
And we need to come up with a
game plan to keep you all safe.
Keep the government from
finding out about your powers.
They already know.
They had specialized cells
used alongside other tactics
to impede whatever powers
someone had.
Mildred had a hood pressed
over her face
so she couldn't use hers.
No, that can't be right.
Jessica hasn't said anything,
and she works there.
Are you feeling okay?
No, we have
to be missing something.
Now, the government
appears to have some sort
of plan beyond freeing us.
You guys are on the inside.
You can help us.
So let's all set our minds
to solving this puzzle.
Together.
Glare
all you want.
While you're staying
under my roof,
I'm gonna learn you
some real discipline.
Don't mind your uncle.
I'll be back faster than
one of your chess games.
But-but I don't want you
to leave at all.
I-I need you.
I'm not leaving forever,
only for a week.
Even if I was,
I'm not worried about you
at all.
Do you want to know why?
Why?
Because you have all the tools
to be on your own and succeed.
Should have figured
you'd catch me.
Don't try to stop me.
I... I wasn't thinking of it.
You can't follow me, either.
I have to do this
on my own. I know.
That's why I brought you this.
How did you know?
Look, when I started this,
I just wanted
to bring you back to me.
I didn't think I could
stand on my own.
I missed how you
made me feel safe.
So you planned that whole thing.
I kind of did, huh?
Look, if I try to keep you here,
it'd be for my needs, not yours.
So please.
Will you be okay?
I have all the tools I need
to be on my own and succeed.
Can you tell me if you see it?
Do I save her?
It's this way. Let's go.
I...
I-I don't know.
I can't see anything.
Just be careful.
I will.
Captioning sponsored by CBS.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org