What a night, y'all.
I mean,
we snuck out to Belle Isle.
Noah, like, nap-timed
the chaperones with his voice,
and Mildred... you floated Rev
like a butterfly.
I have never seen
such trippy stuff sober.
You guys are like superheroes.
Like, with your own origin
story and everything.
I guess that makes me
the Kardashian of the group.
Like, bringing a dash
of reality TV fame
to spice things up.
What's a reality TV?
What's a TV?
TV is like radio you watch
like talkies.
And then reality TV is where
you get, like, a bunch
of regular people
with different personalities,
and you film, like,
all the drama that unfolds.
So, like, for example, so,
like, Shanice... she's our rebel,
so she clashes with Rev,
the golden boy.
And then, Mildred,
you and Hayden are, like,
the "will they, won't they."
Will they, won't they what?
Just wait.
So, then, what are you?
Obviously, I'm the star.
But nobody knows that
because I do not have cameras
following me around anymore.
God, I miss being famous.
Oh, my God, Mariah.
Wh... What?
But how did you get in here?
Does your father
know you're here?
He wasn't gonna let me, but
I-I really wanted to see you. Okay,
but...
How? How are you here?
Some guy. I-I think he said
his name was Hayden.
He opened the door for me,
and... I don't know.
I guess I just...
I really wanted to meet you.
And I didn't think much past...
Making it happen? Yeah.
Hotheaded runs in the family.
Really?
Wow.
Oh, come here.
I love you so much, Mom.
What was that?
What? I...
I...
You...
Um, a-are you okay?
Yeah. Yes, I just...
I...
I really need you to know,
t... to tell you
that you were...
You aremy world.
I never would have left you
by choice.
Okay.
But Dad told me
you wrote a letter,
so... No, I never wrote a letter.
I... You never wrote the letter?
Okay, well, okay, I did, but...
So you just lied to me? No.
It's not like that. I'm just...
I'm-I'm just confused,
and I-I saw...
You have this...
this Bridget person,
and-and... Wow. Okay,
what does Bridget have to do
with you leaving?
I don't know
why I thought I could trust you.
This was a mistake. No, M-Mariah.
Wait. Please.
Just...
This crowd has
doubled since last night.
I just hope
Mariah got home okay.
But how did your
daughter get in?
- She said Hayden let her in.
- I guess that's why
he didn't go to Belle Isle.
He can see the future.
No big deal.
Anyway,
your daughter
sounds like a badass.
It's probably not her first time
sneaking back in at dawn.
Quite the hullabaloo.
And all over us. This is
all good for us, okay?
No publicity is bad publicity
as far as we're concerned.
It keeps us in the public eye
and out of the shadows.
But the government
is a different story.
Steve said they're trying
to have some press event soon.
They want all this to go away.
ASAP.You're on a first-name basis
with the guards?
The papers will be here?
Just Steve.
And we don't really do
paper anymore,
but yes, reporters.
You seem an expert on the press.
Being on camera
used to be my job.
On celluloid film?
Well,
it's digital now, but yeah.
I was actually shooting
my own reality show when...
this happened.
Perhaps
someone documented the
precise moment you were taken,
then. I don't know.
It's all pretty blurry.
I remember drinking a lot
and then arriving on Belle Isle.
I must have been really trashed.
Um, I was shooting
my premiere episode.
This one. Oh, no.
Your body would do nothing
for that dress.
Have you thought more
about me getting my degree?
I think it could be
kind of good for me.
Computer science. What a waste.
You wouldn't even have time, anyway.
Dad thinks I can manage...
Exactly why you know
that's a terrible idea.
Look, being fabulous
is your full-time job now.
Fix your priorities.
And fix your face.
You got a zit coming in.
Cut!
That was harsh, Mom.
Even for the cameras.
Uh-uh, that wasn't for
the cameras. I meant every word.
You need to think
about your brand,
not your brain.
Hey.
Don't worry about
your mom, okay?
This is about you
coming out
of the ex-wives franchise
with your very own spin-off.
You are our future,
right? Our star.
You know what?
If they're gonna bring in
the press,
I'm gonna make myself
the star this show needs.
Hey!
No loitering in the hallways.
Get to breakfast.
I wouldn't eat that.
What is that?
A mate in three puzzle.
It's a way
to play my favorite game
without a set.
Chess. Hayden.
Mildred told me
it's your birthday
tomorrow.
We are gonna party.
How old will you be?
Well, a party
is something to, like,
actually look forward to,
you know? We're
gonna make it sick.
I don't know how or with what,
but, by Gandalf, I'm excited.
Hey, Hay, was I not
supposed to say anything?
Just don't like my birthday.
There was... I mean, is...
Never much to celebrate
when you're locked up.
Your move, bro.
Yo, texpert.
Hey. What's up, J?
Okay, did anybody
pass through here last night
when we were... No.
I checked CCTV
soon as I got your text.
Okay, but then who drew this?
And when?
No idea.
It's a mystery.
On top of the mystery
of what happened at Belle Isle,
well, twice.
Wait, do you have a theory on
what put us to sleep out there?
Working through
Keisha's body cam footage,
but nothing yet.
I should update her.
It'd give us a reason to talk.
These are for you.
Now that we're all
here, tomorrow,
we're holding a press event
to catch the public up
on the 4,400 situation
and dispel any rumors
that have been swirling
around them.
Carla Coleman
from the mayor's office
will be running the event.
Carla.
Thank you, Agent Tanner.
Thanks to the leak,
which DHS is still working on,
the public knows that
4,400 missing persons
appeared on Belle Isle
and are being detained.
That is all they know.
It's gonna be our job
to remind them of that
by removing any space
for speculation.
In your packets, you will see
approved statements,
the reporters in attendance
and an outline of the event.
Agent Tanner also tells me
a few of you
will be tasked with finding
an ambassador among the 4,400.
This is going to be key,
as the public needs
to put a face to the situation.
You want me and Jharrel
to find this person?
Okay, look, my job is
to advocate for the residents,
not to play ball
for some government spin job.
None of the family members
have even been notified.
The mayor believes the sooner
the public has answers,
the sooner we can all focus
on returning the 4,400
to society
and moving on with our lives.
Everybody else, your job
is to get this place cleaned up.
We want the world to see
what a safe
and welcoming environment
we have provided here.
Sorry.
I should have
given you a heads-up.
I-I didn't... No, no.
It's all good.
How have you been?
I'm good. And you?
Actually, I was wondering,
is... is Manny...
I-I know the 4,400
are missing persons.No.
Manny's not a 4,400.
Not officially.
What does that mean?
Look at this.
It's Manny's tag.
Look, this appeared last night.
Only he could have drawn this.
This is a circle.
No. No, this...
It's his signature.
Look, he draws a circle
and the first number,
and then I come in
with a second number,
and we take turns
until there's 12, but...
Look, I think he's here,
and he's trying to
tell me something.
Okay.
So, Manny came back
with the other 4,400
on Belle Isle,
but instead of telling you
he's back,
he's skulking around,
leaving cryptic drawings?
This isn't like before.
This is exactly like before.
Manny went missing
and you got obsessed.
You followed every lead,
and then you made up leads
when those ran dry.
Spent every night at his place
waiting for him to return.
Never coming home.
Carla, I'm sorry.
All right, I know I wasn't great
back then, but...
I'm not gonna give up on him.
And wrecking your whole life,
going on these
wild goose chases...
You really think
that's what Manny
would want for you, Jharrel?
I mean,
you already lost one job.
Well, I'm not losing this one.
This job at this hotel
is the only chance I have
of finding him.
Good luck, Jharrel.
Hey.
There's my favorite
rebel social worker.
FYI, you'll be doing
a tailored statement
at the event tomorrow.
The public likes social workers.
And if I'd rather
jump off a cliff?
Keisha thinks
you're a bleeding heart,
but I think you just don't know
how to be a team player. Oh, I do.
Just not when the game
is rigged.
Look, I need this job,
but I'm here to advocate,
not to be a puppet.
The game has changed.
If you want in,
here's your speech.
Memorize it.
Play ball, or you're out.
Today, we are
interviewing residents
to be potential
press ambassadors.
I think
you might actually be great
at the job.
And it could be fun. A job?
Is this a paid position?
No.
And how would you rate
your oration skills?
Okay.
Gonna take that
as below average.
So,
how do you feel
about public speaking?
Me too.
No worries.
What tactics would you use
with an upset reporter?
Michigan Penal Code.
Article three...
twenty-eight.
A person who commits
unlawful imprisonment
is guilty of a felony punishable
by imprisonment for
not more than 15 years
or a fine
of not more than $20,000.
Or both.
So, you want me,
a Black woman being held
against her will,
to do all this work for free?
Fun.
Oh, geez.
Did you have your interview
for the papers? Nope.
Wasn't asked.
Doubt I have the face they want.
There does seem to be
an air of baloney involved.
But...
when the reporters are around,
if you get nervous,
remember not to sing.
It would be extremely dangerous
if your powers
made the front page.
I can't always help it.
Try?
Is everything all right, Noah?
Where's
your usual joie de vivre?
I-I don't love doctors.
No offense.
Mine haven't been
the most supportive humans
in my life. I see.
Is there anything
I can help you with?
I need this medicine.
I haven't
had it in a week.
I'm transgender.
I need this
to be my true self.
Transgender? Yeah.
When I was born,
they said I was a girl,
but clearly, I-I'm not.
Do you hide this?
It's no secret. I'm proud of it.
I'm out to basically everyone.
Well, this is all...
remarkable.
Sorry, Doc.
Did I blow your mind?
Well, you've...
certainly expanded
my vocabulary.
Thank you for sharing.
And you can count on me
to procure
the medicine you need.
Thanks.
It is such a waste that
they're interviewing everyone
for the press thing when there's
only one real option: Me.
You wantthis role?
Then why weren't you
interviewing
with the rest of us?
Well, I'm waiting
for them to finish
and realize they have no one
so that when they truly need me,
their desperation
will give me the leverage
to get the most out of this.
Oh, like get us
out of here? I'm getting my phone back.
You know they not
gonna let you say the truth.
How we're being held against our will.
I mean, it's not that bad.
It's not like we're in cages.
Not yet.
This is my chance
for me to use my superpower:
My media skills.
But use them for what?
Amen. Same
time tomorrow for prayer.
And for those who haven't heard,
Brother Hayden's
birthday is coming up, and
we'll be having a celebration
- in his honor. All are welcome.
- Looks like
the beginnings of a cult to me.
Claudette.
Glad I caught
you. I could use
your insight
on how to throw a kids' party.
You'd know better than me.
You think that because
I'm a grown woman from my time
that that's what I'd know best?
I didn't mean to offend her. But you did
such a good job at it.
Thought I'd find you here.
Did they audition you, too?
Not yet. They're obviously
gonna use this press event
to screw us over even more.
But...
something else is on your mind.
We need to get out
of this hotel.
And soon. Noah's not
getting the treatment
he needs,
not to mention what the guard
did to him the other day.
And if they find out
about his voice,
about all the... enhancements...
I think I...
When I hugged Mariah,
I saw something.
I think it was
a memory. Her memory.
You believe you might
be experiencing
an emergent ability
akin to Noah? I don't know. I...
I wish I wasn't. I don't want
to be afraid to hug her.
I believe
that with patience and study,
we can identify the boundaries
of all these abilities.
That may offer you
a sense of control.
Yeah, but I'll be no better
at being a mom.
I was so rattled
by the vision
and afraid of losing her
that I lied to her face.
Well,
we're rarely good at something
without practice.
We're only human, after all.
Go easy on yourself.
And when you see her again,
be honest.
And if she never wants
to see me?
I don't think that will happen.
Your situation is
nontraditional, yes,
but there are many ways
to have family.
It's what you make
of it that counts.
Hey, you.
Bridge is bringing home Slows
in, like, five, and, uh,
I get to pick
what we stream tonight.
Okay.
Whoa, whoa. Hold on.
No World War III explosion
about "dad movies"?
What's going on?
You said she wrote a letter,
right?
Right.
I want to read it.
Absolutely not.
It won't help with anything.
And I only told you
about it so that you'd stop
making excuses
for her,
thinking she'd come back.
And she says she never left,
that she was taken. And I
told her she lied
about the letter,
but maybe you were, and... Whoa.
What do you mean,
you told her she was lying?
When did you talk to her?
What did you do?
I went to see her
last night. You did what?
You can ground me later.
Mariah, what were you thinking?
I knew you'd never take me,
so I-I took myself.
I ca...
Well, how'd it go?
Honestly, not great.
I mean, she was nice.
I didn't know
what to call her.
I mean, Bridget is my mom.
I just don't know
what to think anymore.
I need to read that letter.
I need answers.
I'm not interested in being
your master of ceremonies.
What I need
is medical texts,
contemporary medical training.
Just yesterday,
young Noah notified me
of a medication I was unaware of
that he lacks access to.
I would very much like your help
in acquiring it.
Well, I will definitely
work on that.
And on getting Noah the meds
he needs.
So?
You find anyone we could use
as our spokesperson?
Anybody willing
and able? Nope.
Myself included.
But maybe... And hear me out.
Mm-hmm. This whole thing
is a terrible idea.
So, who do you have booked
for hair, makeup and wardrobe?
Yeah,
this isn't that kind of thing.
So, you want us to appear
in front of the press
and the public
like the malnourished,
unjustly held detainees we are?
What do you want? I want what you want.
Good press.
And I have a very particular set
of skills:
Memorization, improvisation
and charming... ization.
Look, I'll even sign an NDA.
It's pretty clear you need me
more than I need you.
You'll sign an NDA?
One demand.
I want my phone back.
Your phone? Yeah, you people
confiscated it.
It's pink
with a rhinestone case and...
Wait, did-did you know
I was coming in here?
What do you mean?
My phone.
There it is. Right there.
Right where?
Look, just get it for me. I can't do that.
Well, then, good luck, sis.Wait.
I can't, but Jessica can.
I'll make the case to her, okay?
Best I can ask for
is supervised time once a week.
Once a day. Twice a week.
Final offer.
Deal.
So, he stood up,
and I was like, "Oh, my God."
Like, wow. I'm so impressed.
And then I stood up,
and I forgot
I was wearing my Louboutins,
and I kid you not, no lie,
I was, like,
a foot taller than this man.
Like, like, I could fit
one of his Grammys
in between our heads.
Cut!
Hi. Excuse me.
I know you're working.
I-I just noticed those...
those lighting stands and cables
could be tidied up, you know?
Like, someone could trip
and get really hurt, so...
This is my first solo show,
and I really want to avoid
any legal drama.
And also for nobody to die.
So if we could just...
LaDonna, honey, remember,
you're a butterfly.
Don't bother yourself
with the worker bees.
Now, come away from the window.
You can't afford
to get any darker.
Sharon, are we ready to roll?
We're ready to roll.
Okay, let's get this over with.
Can't give a girl
some accessories?
These eyes are not
gonna highlight themselves.
Time to be a butterfly.
They couldn't vacuum
two days ago?
Well, isn't all this just fine
and dandy for the cameras.
Can you believe LaDonna
is working for the enemy?
Oh, let her have this.
She's smarter
than she appears
and more current
than the two of us.
Speak for yourself.
I know enough
to know when I'm
being bamboozled.
Excuse me,
unhand this young man.
Can't. Orders.
Where exactly
are you taking him?
And why don't you take
your hands off him
while you think of your answer.
They said I have to leave
to get my meds.
That makes no sense.
Others have been treated
here, so why is he
being singled out? You can take it
up with Agent Tanner.
It's her request.
Noah.
Remember what we discussed.
We'll see you soon.
They can do anything
they want to us.
All in the name of good press.
They didn't want the reporters
seeing his face
and forcing them to explain it.
I should have protected him.
I should have known
not to trust them.
This wasn't your fault.
We're all doing
the best we can in here
in the face of people
who only want
the best for themselves.Mm.
And LaDonna's about to do
their job for them.
Welcome,
everyone. I'm Carla Coleman
from the mayor's office.
To be clear,
we will not be releasing
any personal information
at this time.
Our goal is to keep
our residents secure
until it is deemed
safe for them to rejoin society.
Got it?
Good. Okay,
let me introduce you
to our resident,
since I'm sure you'd rather hear
from her than me.
Hi, everyone.
I'll be your hostess, LaDonna.
Please follow me.
So, as you can see,
Bois Blanc and the government
know how to treat their guests.
Where are the others? Are there recreational
areas? Of course, but the government
has to respect
everybody's privacy.
I noticed
a fleet of guards on duty.
Aren't
their little outfits cute?
I swear,
I feel like Michelle Obama
with my own Secret Service.
Things have been very scary
and confusing,
but with the government agencies
taking care of us, we have felt
safe and-and cared for.
Uh, Tom Ramirez with the
Detroit Express-Ledger.
You are LaDonna Landry, right?
I-I am. Did you recognize me?
Your mother said that you went
to rehab when you left the set
of your show six years ago.
You look great, like you haven't
- aged a day. What's your secret?
- Tom,
you know the answer.
It is
my amazing 11-step skin care
regimen.
Now I'd like you to hear
from our social worker,
Jharrel Mateo.
Thank you, uh,
LaDonna, and...
friends, for joining us.
Uh, "As a social worker
"for the 4,400,
"I take great pride
"in working alongside
the agencies
to prioritize
our guests' welfare."
Look, this whole thing
is personal to me.
My brother is a missing person,
so I know
how hard it is.
And I hope the day
will come soon
when we are finally allowed
to inform family members
instead of keeping them and
the public at large in the dark
about holding these innocent people
against their will. Thank you, Jharrel.
Always sticking up for us.
Jharrel, can you expand more?
Sorry, Tommy,
but we do have a schedule.
So, we're gonna go
to the dining room next.
Wait until you see the spread.
We have lobster.
All righty. Right this way.
Looks like you won't have
that unstable
partner much longer.
Really, Jharrel?
Look, I don't lie for a living,
all right?
Maybe this whole thing
is a lot easier for you
than it is for me.
Of course you think
this is about being the hero.
You're not the only one
with something to lose here.
If this blows back on the mayor,
it is my head. And I'm sorry.
All right? I didn't mean
to hurt you or your job.
I... Well, you did.
And it still didn't
bring Manny back.
I can fix this.
You don't know how
to fix anything.
There she is.
The woman of the hour.
What can I do for you?
I'm just here for my phone.
I'm sure when people watch,
they're gonna be texting me.
My...
My dad's gonna freak.
Look,
I have to stick my neck
way out to even get my hands
on it, so... Okay,
that's not what we agreed.
First of all, the phone is mine.
Like, I... Like, I own it.
It became government property
when you came to Belle Isle.
I didn't come, I was taken. Look,
you did a great job today.
It's gonna help your cause.
Auntie Cha Cha!
You made it! Hey, girl. Come here.
What are you doing here,
Cha Cha?
If I recall, you
weren't invited.
Not by you.
But it's not your party, is it?
Come give your godmother a hug,
girl.
Stay away from her.
This is her day, not yours.
I don't like your tone.
It's disrespectful. Sharon, what is this?
This is trailer gold.
Don't worry, if it's good for
the show, it's good for you.
Hon, have a mai tai.
Okay?
Uh, B-cam, are you getting this?
You don't talk to me
like that...♪ 'Bout that bass, no treble
We'll try again in a few days.
Right.
Where are you, bro?
I miss you.
What the...?
Carla told me where to find you.
After your
meltdown about your brother,
she knew you'd be here.
So, this is Manny's place, huh?
You could've just called.
I know.
You knew you could get fired
if you tanked the press thing.I...
Well, I can't help you
if you don't care. No, I do care.
All right?
That's why I said what I said.
Really? Because acting out
didn't seem to help
the 4,400 so much
as your own conscience.
All right...
How did you
keep yourself together
after you lost your sister?
My job.
It helped me focus on something
other than myself.
I think I need that. You do.
Look, you want to be there
for them, be there for them.
They already went missing once.
It's not fair
they go missing again.
Let go.
Oh, my God.
Is everything okay?
Excuse me, Officer Taylor
said we'd have some privacy.
The guards seem friendly.
You know,
we saw the press piece they ran.
It is ridiculous
how the public's
already eating this up. Yeah, LaDonna
shouldn't have
done that.
Um, hey, listen.
Mariah
has something
she'd like to say to you.
I'll leave her to it.
No. Dad, wait. Don't go.
Yeah?
"Dear Logan...
"I'm so sorry,
but I can't do this.
"I tried. I promise I tried,
"but I realize I'm not
meant to be a mother.
"You and Mariah
deserve better than me.
"You have always been my heart,
and I know you will be that
for our child."
"I meant every vow that I made
"to you.
"I'm only sorry
"that I'm not strong enough
to keep them.
Shanice."
Mariah.
Logan,
I had no idea
that you would ever read
that letter.
That it would stay with you
for 16 years.
I'm so sorry.
It was a difficult time,
and I-I was scared.
But I'm here now,
and I'd like to start from here.
If you'll let me.
I really hope you will.
Hey, Doc.
Brought these medical texts
for you.
Oh, my.
Thank you.
Who is the physician from whom
you were able to borrow these?
My brother's, Manny.
He wasn't a doctor or anything.
More a polymath,
before he went missing.
I'm... very sorry to hear that.
Might he be among us 4,400?
I had hoped.
Thought I saw a green light
out the window the night
he went missing
and everything, but...
he's not here.
You're sure you want me
to have these?
Yeah.
It's time.
It's right in here.
Um, who are you, again?
Like, am I getting disappeared?
'Cause I just wanted
my phone back.
Oh, no, no, I'm not Gestapo.
I'm Soraya.
I've been trying to get
you alone for a couple days now,
but you were busy, but then...
I found the pilot rough cut
lurking on the deep Internet.
I figured you'd
never seen it and...
Wait, nerd lady, the pilot
to That LaDonna Life? Uh-huh.
Are you saying
you know who I am? Of course.
You're Loretta Landry's
daughter.
I have been watching
you since season five
of Real Ex-Wives of Miami.
I was so excited
for That LaDonna Life
to air, but then
you disappeared
and they said you went to rehab.
I always thought
that you changed your name
and snuck off to MIT
because in season nine,
episode seven of Real-Ex,
you mentioned
computer engineering
and your 4.6 GPA, but...
turns out that you were
just part of an inexplicable
physics-defying phenomenon
with 4,399 others.
You're, like,
my very first stan.
Oh. Honor.
Check it out.
Ba-bam.
Peace.
Not everyone can have this life.
But everyone wants it.
Auntie Cha Cha, you made it!
Baby girl, come here!
What are you doing?
I don't like your tone.
It's disrespectful.
And I don't let anyone
disrespect me.
No, honey, you disrespected
yourself in that outfit.
What did you say to me?
Did I stutter?
Ladonna knows I don't...
Mom.
What are you doing?
You should be thanking me.
For stealing my show?
For giving you one.
You are not enough on your own.
Reality TV needs
real-life drama,
and Cha Cha and I bring it.
I thought you were smart
enough to know that.
Oh, honey... you're crying.
Good, I'll go get the cameras.
You are unbelievable!
Suit yourself.
Cha Cha, take three!
No, no, no, no, no, you
don't walk away from me!
You come here, you want
to come crashing parties,
you come and talk to me!
I asked them to pick these up.
I'll do it myself.
It's my show.
You need to talk
to me first! Hey!
You better take your hand
off of me. The nerve.
Somebody bring me my drink so
I can throw it on this woman...
Okay then.
I will bring
the real-life drama.
How's this? Right there is excellent.
Surprised to see me following
through on my promises?
I am.
My husband was
a preacher like you.
He did things for show.
Or for himself.
Well, that's not me.
But he sounds like my father.
So...
uh, what can I help out with?
Well, actually,
we're just finishing up.
He should be here...
Happy birthday!
This is the best we could do.
Can't even find
a light anywhere.
Oh, I, I can help with that.
Look, I get it.
I messed up, but...
at least I can
kind of light this candle.
Wow.Ooh.
It's a very nice light,
thank you.
What're you gonna wish for,
Hayden?
I wish...
I wish Noah was here.
But... but you all
have made this day
better than it should have been.
Thank you.
I mean, there's
a lobster with a candle
in its head. Come on.
Yeah, I think that is
the wisest course of action.
Great, thank you.
Bye-bye.
That was the mayor's office.
Apparently Jharrel
keeps his job.
They don't want it
to appear retaliatory.
I can't say that I'm upset.
He shouldn't have said it
when he said it,
but he was only saying
the truth.
God, you're defending him?
He's my partner. But he's
not your only partner.
Yeah, well,
my other partner reneged
on a deal I made with LaDonna.
You couldn't just let her
have some supervised time
with the phone, really?
Do you not understand
the pressure
that I'm under
with these people?
It would be nice if my partner
of six months would be
on my side for once,
instead of the colleague
she met last week.
Okay, fine.
I'm gonna go back
to my place tonight.
I think we need some time
to cool off. Really?
Do you like it?
You made me a chess set.
You saw that coming, didn't you?
Hey, Millie?
I think I like birthdays now.
Good.
Want to play chess?
So the bad news is I remember
what I was doing
the moment the green light
snatched me up.
I was falling off a roof...
drunk,
shooting my own reality show
and no one
noticed. Oh, my.
And the good? I didn't die?
Oh, and what good news
that is, my dear.
It would be a mighty loss,
a woman of your intellect.
Literally no one has ever said
that to me before.
But you're right, I-I am smart.
About time somebody noticed.
I see your extraordinary worth,
LaDonna.
Now...
Jharrel loaned me
medical journals.
And perhaps you
could help me refine
my understanding of DNA?
Sure.
All right.
Let's see...
What is this?
Okay, I don't know
what it means,
but it looks like
some old computer language.
My first thought is Cobol, which
no one's used since the '70s.
Well, these books belonged
to Jharrel's brother.
He went missing,
too. Jharrel
also mentioned the
presence of a green light,
but Manny isn't among the 4,400.
It could be nothing.
A missing person,
connected even loosely to us,
with computer codes
from the past lying around?
Sounds like something.
Could Manny be involved
in our plight some way?
Or this could lead us to him.
Seems worth looking into.
We certainly have the time.
PR lady?
Hi, Mariah, I'm Ladonna,
one of the 4,400
here with your mother,
and I need your help.
I've sent you a video
that I need you to put on blast.
To help Shanice.
To help all of us.
Look, I know you're
a bad-ass like your mom.
And I know what people
will do for their moms.
So thank you for doing
the right thing.
I didn't do anything.
I don't know
why this happened to me.
Do you see that? You know what,
I wouldn't eat that.
You want to tell me when you
plan on letting us out of here
for good? Michigan penal code,
article 328:
A person who commits
unlawful imprisonment
is guilty of a felony.
What?
Why in the world
would you attack him?
He didn't do anything!
Everybody needs to understand
that order will be maintained!
You don't make the rules here.
We do.
"Restrain" means
to confine that person
so as to interfere
with that person's liberty
without lawful authority.
Captioning sponsored by CBS.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org