Trudy, I'm home! And I'm hungry.
What's for dinner, baby?
I don't know, Oscar.
Whatever you're cooking.
Cooking?
What are you talking about cooking?
Cooking is a woman's job.
(SCREAMS IN HIGH-PITCHED VOICE)
On second thought, I'll order a pizza.
I'm starving. What's for dinner, Mama?
I don't know, Penny.
Whatever you're cooking.
Cooking? That's a mama's job.
(SHRIEKS)
I think I'll order pizza.
Got 'em on the phone right now.
What do you want?
Ooh, give me a veggie pizza.
Veggie pizza? What are you...
Not in my house.
Give me two Meat Lovers with extra meat.
Y'all still got
that delicious buffalo sauce?
What are you doing, Mama?
I'm tracing my family roots
on the Where My People At? app.
You can't know yourself unless you know
where you come from, honey.
Oh, man. Trudy,
you Parkers sure got around.
Your papa and your mama
were rolling stone.
-(GROWLING)
-(YELPS)
Wow, Mama. The Parkers lineage
goes all the way to Africa.
What about Daddy's family?
What? You don't know?
The Prouds are descendants
of African kings and queens.
Show 'em, Trudy.
(SCATTING)
Dang, Daddy, where your people at?
(SINGING) The... Proud... Family... What?
You and me will always be tight
Family every day and every night
Even when you start acting like a fool
You know that I'm lovin'
every single thing you do
I know I can always be myself
When I'm with you
more than anybody else
Every single day
that I'm headed off to school
You know there's no one
I love as much as you
-The family
Proud family
They'll make you scream!
They'll make you wanna sing!
It's a family thing, a family
A proud, proud family
Proud family
They'll push your buttons!
They'll make you wanna hug 'em
A family, family
Proud, proud family
(OSCAR SCREAMS)
(KIDS SQUEALING AND LAUGHING)
Hey, Trudy, what's for...
-(GROWLS)
-(GASPS)
We'll order another pizza.
Mama, are you okay?
I'm great.
You won't believe what I discovered.
It cost me more than $1,000 in clues,
but I tracked down Suga Mama's people.
$1,000?
Alex Haley found Kunta Kinte,
Chicken George and Halle Berry for less.
Be quiet, Oscar.
Did you know Suga Mama's
real name is Charlette?
I thought it was Beelzebub.
TRUDY: Oscar, you've been holding out.
You never told me
your people were from Oklahoma.
OSCAR: I didn't know
Suga Mama even had people.
The only people I knew was Ray Ray
and them on my daddy's side.
-Boy, what was on your daddy side, boy?
-My good looks. (LAUGHS)
Yeah. It skipped you
and went straight to my Bobby.
Ain't that right, baby?
(SINGING) I'm pretty, pretty, pretty
Suga Mama, Suga Mama, I was just on
the Where My People At? app,
and when I clicked on your name...
Wait, wait, wait. Where y'all been?
Mama took me back-to-school shopping
at the swap meet.
(SINGING)
I got a do-rag and some cheap cologne
And 18 pair of white tube socks
You haven't been
back-to-school in 55 years.
Quit hating, dawg.
(SINGING)
Because I'm pretty, pretty, pretty
See, Mama, that's what I'm talking about.
This proves that
you like Bobby better than me.
Ooh, you sure are slow, boy.
So, Trudy, you clicked on my name
and what happened?
It says here you were born
and raised in Oklahoma.
I thought you were born
and raised in Jurassic Park.
(LAUGHS AND SNARLS)
I don't want to talk about it.
Oh, you not going to check
Oscar's chin, Ma?
-I don't want to talk about it.
-But Suga Mama...
I told you, Trudy,
I don't want to talk about it!
I tell you one thing
you're going to talk about, old woman.
Why didn't you get me ice cream
and new clothes?
Whoa, what is wrong with Suga Mama?
I don't know, baby. Oscar?
How would I know? Maybe she's
the fugitive from The Fugitive.
-WOMAN ON TV: The tension is palpable.
-(COMPUTER CHIMES)
TRUDY: Hey, everybody, look at this.
We've been invited to Suga Mama's
family reunion in Towne,
Oklahoma, in three weeks.
This is a sign. Family, we have to go.
Why would I go anywhere
where there might be more Suga Mamas?
And I got a gig that weekend.
You got a paying gig, Bobby?
(SINGING) If I win, first place
is all-you-can-eat nachos
That would be a no.
So it's decided. We're going.
Uh-uh. I can't go, Mama.
We're going on a class trip
to Washington, D.C. in three weeks.
Daddy already paid for my trip.
About that, baby girl.
Mr. Chips wrote that check
from the Proud Family snack account,
and I don't know what he did,
but it bounced.
Now you owe the school a $25 service fee.
That settles it. No more excuses.
-We're all going.
-SUGA MAMA: Well, I ain't going.
Not now, not ever.
And there ain't nothing
that any of y'all can do
to make me change my mind.
(CHILDREN CLAMORING)
I hate you...
(SINGING) Yeah, yeah, yeah
Shabooya, roll call
Shabooya, yeah, yeah
-My name is Oscar
-Yeah
-I make Proud Snacks.
-Yeah.
-Men call me Snack Master
-Yeah
-Women call me Snack Mac
-Roll call
What women would that be, Oscar?
-Which ones?
-You. (LAUGHS)
And only you, you know that. Come on.
-My name is Trudy
-Yeah
-I am the boss
-'Cause I be running things
-Yeah
-Because I got that sauce
-Roll call
Shabooya, yeah, yeah
Shabooya, roll call
-My name is Bobby
-Yeah
-I'm here to say
-I love my nachos
-Yeah
-With guacamole
-Roll call
Shabooya, yeah, yeah
Shabooya, roll call
-I is Bebe
-Yeah
-And I am Cece
We got to pee-pee
What?
So stop the hoopty
I miss you so much, Penny.
Aw, I miss you more.
I really wish
you were going with us to D.C.
-Yeah.
-(GASPS)
Too bad your daddy's
monkey's check bounced.
But don't worry,
there will be other school trips.
Come on, Kareem. Bye-bye, Proud.
Penny, I'll call you later, okay?
Oh! I can't stand her!
-My name is Penny
-Yeah
-I'm here to say
-LaCienega's gonna pay
-Yeah
If she steals my bae
ALL: Huh?
Oh-oh. Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Look here. Oscar, we're here.
TRUDY: Wow. This looks deserted.
PENNY: Does anybody still live here?
(VOICE ECHOES)
I should have known.
All of Suga Mama's people are bums.
We drove 3,000 miles for nothing.
Suga Mama, you owe me gas money!
And a lot of it, too.
Wow. I guess that's that.
Well, we tried, family.
Might as well turn around.
And go to Washington, D.C.
Daddy, please. Please, Daddy, please.
No. We're going to the Snack Hall of Fame
in Topeka, Kansas.
I should've been inducted years ago.
(SINGING) The Old Towne Road
I hate that song.
No, the sign, baby bro.
(SPITS)
Oscar, that's it. Turn down that road.
Come on, Trudy.
If we leave now, we can get
to the Snack Hall of Fame before dinner.
They got free fish sticks and tater tots.
(SCREAMS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
PENNY: Wow!
This is amazing.
OSCAR: It's amazing if you own it.
If you're a sharecropper
like Suga Mama and her people,
you just picking up
a whole lot of cow poop.
Ah, what there?
"Deuteronomy Leviticus
D'Brickashaw Ferguson
"Karl Anthony Towne, founder."
Who's this, Mama?
TRUDY: Wow, this is a statue
of Suga Mama's granddaddy.
Wait. What? Suga Mama's granddaddy?
That ain't no statute, that's him.
When he first laid eyes on Suga Mama,
he froze in his steps.
-(CHUCKLES)
-(SPITTING)
You just keep on laughing, boy.
I'm gonna dot both of your eyes.
(HORSE NEIGHS)
Whoa, whoa!
What are you folks doing here?
Don't you know
that this is private property?
Bobby, I think this nice mountain of a man
wants to talk to you.
UNCLE BOBBY: Nah, baby, bro.
(SINGING) I'm a lover, not a fighter
-But you might want to cut down model.
-No, you talk to him.
Enough, city slickers.
This is Towne de Roselyn.
Unless your last name is Towne,
you better get up on outta here.
What's going on here, boys?
Don't worry, Pa. We got it handled.
Yeah, Pa, these nice folks
were just leaving.
Wait, wait. Wait a minute, now.
We're Suga Mama's...
I mean, Charlette's kids.
We're Townes, too.
Hey, Pa, look on the roof
of that contraption.
Little Bit.
Yeah, it's me. Hi, Pa.
Good to see you again.
Hmm...
I thought I told you
to never come back here.
(ALL GASP)
Giddy-up.
Hey, where y'all going?
It's our sister, Charlette.
Yeah, we saw, and she didn't age well.
Hyah!
Well, Trudy, I guess that's that.
Suga Mama's daddy don't like her
any more than we do.
Let's go get some free fish sticks.
Ooh, I thought I'd never, ever say
these words, but I agree with Oscar.
Let's get the heck out of Oklahoma.
No, we are here to discover
who we are as a family.
We know who we are, Trudy.
We're the Prouds.
You, on the other hand,
being from Boujeeville,
-you just don't understand.
-Look, we're not going anywhere.
You've been outvoted, Trudy.
Bobby, Penny, strap her to the roof.
You can ride inside, Suga Mama,
but don't get used to it.
(SCREAMS)
(HONKING)
Hey, everybody. I'm Myrtle.
I've been with your pa for years.
I'm the one who really
runs things around here.
-(SQUAWKS)
-(BARKS)
What you doing?
Everybody's in the back
waiting to meet you. Come on in.
Sorry, Frontier Stacey Abrams,
but we were just...
On our way in.
Look, Trudy, we voted. Ow!
And you won by a landslide.
You gonna pull it off!
Hmmph!
(OSCAR GROANING)
(SIZZLING)
Don't just stand there, y'all.
Go fix yourselves a plate.
I got beans, greens, potatoes, tomatoes,
squash, yam, lamb, hams,
pigs, ribs, steak, shrimp,
chicken, turkey, gravies, pies.
You name it.
You ain't gotta tell me twice.
(SINGING) 'Cause the food sure look nice
Put some gravy on my rice
I know it's been a long time
since you left, Charlette,
so let me just point out everybody.
(PUFF WHINES)
Now, that's Charles
and Charlie's boys in the band.
Charles son, June Bug,
and Charlie's boy, Man.
Over here, June Bug's wife, Germaine,
and their 14-year-old daughter, Harriet.
And over there is Man's wife, Peaches.
Ain't she cute?
-That's their 14-year-old son, Man-Man.
-(CHEERING)
And over here last, but not least,
is your baby brother, Chuck.
Say hi, Chuck.
(LAUGHS)
I've been waiting a long time
to meet you, Charlette.
I heard so many stories about you.
Well, I ain't heard any stories about you.
That's because I was born
after Pops threw you out.
Who the heck told you that?
Well, you know,
everybody knows that story. (SLURPS)
I forgot. Why don't you refresh my memory,
baby brother?
You know, you thought you were too good,
that you didn't know your place.
What? I didn't know my place?
Who the heck told you that?
And over here is Chuck's beautiful family.
His wife, Raquel, and their baby twins,
Tika and... Where's Tiko?
-Where's Bebe?
-(BULL BELLOWS)
(BELLOWS)
My baby!
(ALL GASP)
(SCREAMING)
-Somebody do something!
-Huh?
(BOTH YELP)
RAQUEL: That was a close one.
Always getting in trouble.
(ALL GASP)
Here you go, Grandpa Towne.
You can call me Pa.
(ALL APPLAUDING)
Gracias for saving Tiko, cousin Oscar.
I'm really proud of you, Oscar.
Whoo-whee! (LAUGHS)
That slim's a natural cowboy.
Looks like we've finally
got some competition
for the Towne Family Rodeo Championship.
(ALL CHEERING)
Not bad for a city boy.
Little Bit, at least you did
one thing right.
-Come on, grandson.
-(GRUMBLES)
Let me show you the piece of land
that you're going to inherit
from me one day.
(BLUBBERS) I just...
I don't know why I'm crying.
Is this what real
parental love feels like?
(SOBBING)
No. This is what
love feels like, baby bro.
(SINGING) You better get you
some of these ribs St. Louis style
You know my favorite
Nacho bridge in king's highway
Maybe if I hold my hand higher...
I think I got a bar! I think I got a bar!
Hello? Hello, Kareem?
-(GRUMBLES)
-Girl, that ain't gonna work.
You guys don't get
cell service around here?
No, we can get it, but Grandpa blocks it.
Yep. He thinks cell phones
are foolishness.
What?
You got to go clear to Texas
just to make a phone call.
(SPITTLE CLANGS)
Ugh!
So what do you guys
do around here for fun?
-Go to the swimming hole.
-Hole?
-Skip rocks.
-Skip what?
-Knit.
-Mama! Can I holler at you right quick?
Mama, we got to get up out of here.
Penny, I'm personally glad
your phone isn't working.
Take this time to go learn
something about your family.
I did. I learned I don't like them.
Or you right now.
What did you say, young lady?
I ain't say nothing, ma'am.
You mind if I sit in?
Not at all, cuz.
Where do I plug it in at?
No, cuz, I'm the only one
who play guitar around here.
Give this a try, cuz. I love that for you.
(SCRAPING WOOD)
I feel like Washboard Chaz.
Whoa! Whoa!
-Help! Easy, now!
-(PLUCKING SOFTLY)
All right, slim, be careful.
Old Killer here
has thrown his last five riders.
(MAN YELLS AND GRUNTS)
Well, Uncle Charlie,
there's no need for a sixth one.
-Too late.
-(GULPS)
(SHOUTING)
Trudy!
(LAUGHING)
Yee-ha!
(PLAYING SONG)
Little Bit, why do you always got to prove
you're better than everybody?
Not everybody, Big Head Charles, just you.
(SCREAMS)
(LAUGHS)
Guess you can add water-skiing
to that list!
(SCREAMS)
(ENGINES REVVING)
(LAUGHS)
(CHEERS)
Congratulations, Majestic.
You are the proud mother
of a brand-new foal.
(SINGING) They call me Uncle Bobby
Singing is my hobby
If you think I'm crazy,
you don't want to meet my family
-(SQUEALS)
-Uh-oh. Another one?
Might need an Altoid
'Cause I keep it funky
When I talk and check the tabloids
I'm too hot, baby
I can't stop, lady
I sing like Rick James
But I could have been an athlete
All this money might build
Another Black Wall Street
I'm gonna take my horse
to the old town road
I'm gonna ride till I can't no more
I'm gonna take my horse
to the old town road
Got to ride the horse
if you're gonna get away
Giddy-up, giddy-up
That boy is a true Towne.
Come on in, Penny. The water is just fine.
That's okay, Man-Man.
I'm good. Look a little dangerous.
No, it isn't. It's fun. Come on, girl.
Okay. Okay.
(GRUMBLES)
Whee! (SCREAMS)
-(SCREAMS)
-(LAUGHING)
What is that?
(SCREAMING)
Okay!
SUGA MAMA: Come on, Big Head.
You know you don't want none of this.
You never could beat me
at thumb wrestling.
Well, I was a little boy then, Charlette.
Now I'm a grown man.
No, you're a doomed man.
Argh! You cheated!
Ha-ha! That's it. Right, Big Head?
That's what all y'all
gonna be doing tomorrow
when I win the Towne Family
Rodeo championship.
You're not going to be in the rodeo,
Little Bit. Nothing's changed.
No girls allowed.
(MEN LAUGHING)
(BOY CRYING)
Quit your messing around.
Stop all that crying. Towne men don't cry.
We got to get ready for the junior rodeo.
I told Hurricane here
to take it easy on you.
Okay. Now hold on, like I showed you.
(WHIMPERS)
(SOBBING)
Oh! Get up.
You're not hurt. Act like a Towne.
My grandpa won that junior rodeo,
my pa won,
I won, and it's a Towne tradition.
And you're gonna win if I have to strap...
Hey, Pa, I could do it!
Yee-haw!
Whoo-hoo!
See, Pa, you don't have to worry,
I'll keep up the Towne tradition.
No girls allowed. You know that.
Now go in the house and cook dinner.
I'm hungry.
Oh! You'll never change, Pa.
I can't stand you.
(SNIFFLES)
(BARKS)
Come on, Puff.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)