(CHATTERING)
-BOY 1: Hey, hold up, wait up!
-GIRL 1: Watch out!
-Hold on, where is everybody going'?
-Where do you think, Proud?
-To see Makeup Boy at the mall.
-Who?
Makeup Boy!
Where have you been, Penny?
He's only the biggest
makeup influencer on the planet!
All right, basics, listen up.
You want to slim down those chubby cheeks,
hide that fivehead,
and cover up them nasty pimples.
-(SCOFFS)
-MAKEUP BOY: And when you're finished,
set with my sold-out setting spray
and get ready to slay.
Uh-uh!
Normally, I sell this-ish for $35,
but if you swipe up now and use my code
"Makeup Boy" in all caps,
and make sure it's all caps, sis,
'cause it's not gonna work,
you can get it for $34.99.
Is he serious? You guys aren't falling'
for this-ish, are you?
Ninety-six, Ninety-seven,
Ninety-eight, Ninety-nine.
-Penny, you think you can loan me $34?
-No!
Hey, you'll! We better get to the mall.
The line's gonna be too long.
Makeup Boy is signing autographs
for only $20.
PENNY: Wow, Maya.
You're the last person I thought
would be into makeup.
You being all-natural and everything.
Girl, please, this look is a process.
Besides, there's nobody more woke
than Makeup Boy.
Well, he certainly
didn't wake up like that.
-Zang.
-Don't be a hater, Penny.
Why?
Because I won't give someone
$20 for an autograph
because they're trending?
Because I'm not trying to hide behind
a faceful of foundation and lip gloss?
Because I have a mind of my own?
You should really consider hiding that
face behind something, Proud.
Maybe then you'd have more than
your mum and dad as followers on Hologram.
-Holla.
-DIJONAY: Come on, y'all,
I got my little brother holding a place
in line for us at the mall.
-Et tu, Dijonay?
-No, I haven't eaten yet.
What is that on your forehead?
So, Makeup Boy says, "Wearing' duct tape
five-minutes a day
keeps the wrinkles away."
Dijonay, you're only 14.
We don't have wrinkles.
-ALL: And we never will!
-Hey!
You coming' with us, Penny?
Nah, I'm gonna do something
a little more useful with my $20.
-Hey!
-Like burn it.
MYRON: Can't see anything.
(BLOWING)
Come on, guys, I got my 20. Let's go.
(EXCLAIMING)
I can't believe I just did that.
Can I have my glasses back,
please? Whoever you...
(GROANING)
(SINGING) The... Proud... Family... What?
You and me will always be tight
Family every day and every night
Even when you start acting like a fool
You know that I'm loving'
every single thing you do
I know I can always be myself
When I'm with you more than anybody else
Every single day
that I'm headed off to school
You know there's no one
I love as much as you
The family the family
Proud family
They'll make you scream
They'll make you wanna sing
It's a family thing, a family
a proud, proud family
Proud family
They'll push your buttons!
They'll make you wanna hug them.
A family a family proud, proud family
Proud, proud family
(OSCAR SCREAMS)
TRUDY: Oh, Oscar.
(TRUDY AND OSCAR LAUGHING)
Oh, I can't stand them!
-Hi, Penny.
What were y'all doin'?
-Nothing, baby.
(CLEARS THROAT)
-What're you upset about, Penny?
-My friends.
They're all at the mall giving
Makeup Boy $20 for an autograph.
Oh, yeah, that boy who gives makeup tips.
A boy that does makeup?
What is your generation coming to, Penny?
I don't know, Daddy. They're like zombies.
They do what any random noob
tells them to do.
Relax, Penny. We did the same thing
when I was a kid.
Everybody used to dress up like Prince.
The girls and the boys.
-Who's Prince?
(LAUGHS)
Okay, gather round, y'all.
Let Daddy tell you about Prince.
Baby, it's easy
(EXCLAIMS)
Trudy!
Dig if you will the picture
Of you and I engaged in a kiss
The sweat of your body covers me
Yeah, can you my darling?
Can you picture this?
Dream, if you can, a courtyard
An ocean of violets in bloom
Animals strike curious poses
They feel the heat
The heat between me and you
How can you just leave me standing
Alone in a world that's so cold? So cold
Maybe you're just too demanding
Ah! Trudy!
Maybe I'm just like my father, too bold
Maybe you're just like my...
(EXCLAIMS)
What is that on your forehead?
Yeah, I got it at the mall
from that Makeup Boy.
-Whoo! That fella sure know his stuff.
-You too, Suga Mama?
MAKEUP BOY: All right, I'm only gonna
say it once, so listen up.
The lip color of
the month, basics, is blue.
But not just any blue, my blue.
And to get my blue,
I need to see some green.
The baddest has spoken.
This is sad.
All you need is a stupid video
and three likes,
and suddenly, the whole world
wants to follow you?
SUGA MAMA: Penny! Penny, baby!
Come on down here
and clean your Suga Mama dentures.
-Yuck! It's Wednesday already?
-SUGA MAMA: I heard that.
Sorry, Suga Mama. I'm coming.
(CHUCKLES) You know what? I'll show them.
Hey, y'all. I'm Penny, and welcome to
the premiere of Growing' Up Proud.
Question, have you ever had to
clean your grandmama's dentures?
(SNORING)
(YELPS)
(WHACKING SOUNDS)
Come back here.
(SCREAMS)
(BARKS)
(GROWLING)
What?
Come back here!
(YELPING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS, SNORES)
(CHUCKLES)
Hey!
(PHONE BEEPS)
(BEEPS REPEATEDLY)
OSCAR: Penny!
Penny, since when did
you start wearing' dentures?
Lose a fight at school, baby girl?
No, Daddy. What are you talking' about?
These boxes are addressed to you, Penny.
It must be a mistake. I didn't... Snap!
-(EXCLAIMS) Oh snap.
-(PHONE BEEPS)
Ooh wee!
Minty Fresh Mr. Denture, my favorite.
Papi, I think I died and gone to heaven.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(LAUGHING)
Put your chompers back in
your head, Suga Mama. This is for Penny.
Well, what happened to my grandbaby?
You lose a fight at school
like your daddy?
No, actually I think I won.
I made a video of me cleaning your
dentures to prove a point to my friends
that anybody can get followers,
and I was right.
Oh, I can't wait to rub it in their faces.
And I can't wait to rub this into my grin.
(WHIRRING)
Bam! 10,000 followers in one day.
What did I tell you?
Wham! Makeup Boy got 50,000
in the time it took you to say, "Bam."
Shazam! (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Who cares about dentures anyway?
Apparently, enough people
to make my video go viral.
Enough old people.
-Congratulations, Martha Stewart.
-Who?
Some grandma who makes cakes
and hangs out with this granddaddy
rapper named Snoopy.
NUBIA: His name is Snoop Dogg.
He our cousin, nephew.
And he produced our latest track,
which we selling' for $19.99.
But we don't have money for a CD.
We're broke.
We ain't doing' no CDs.
We do wax. We old school.
Well, Nubia, we're broke school.
We gave all our money
to Makeup Boy yesterday.
Proud didn't.
Really, LaCienega? It's like that now?
Nah, uh-uh, keep your skrilla, Proud.
What you gonna do
is drop our track on your next video.
That was just a one-time thing, Nubia.
I was just proving a point.
Hey, Proud, you done seen that
Bottle Cap Challenge?
(DISCO MUSIC PLAYING)
(SCREAMS)
Well, Olei gonna do that with your head.
(GROWLING)
Uh, I could probably do one more video.
(ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(SCRATCHING SOUNDS)
Ouch!
Rochelle, play the turntable!
Girl, what's a turntable?
Whoa, now. Hold on, baby girl.
I'll show you how to do that.
See, this and an eight-track
was all we needed back in the day.
I'd go to your mother's house,
turn the lights down low,
put on some Switch...
PENNY: Ooh, and then what?
OSCAR: Her father'd turn on the lights,
put on Shirley Caesar,
and throw my Black butt out.
Trudy!
Those were the days.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(SCREAMS)
Take them. I hope you didn't pay for this,
baby girl.
Hands up, cash out
Here to take all you have
Hands up yeah give me all your cash
No fuss just put it in the bag
Gross Sisters we gonna have the last laugh
Hands up cash out
here to take all you have
Hey, good looking out, Proud.
Drake, Cardi B, and Bruno Mars
done reached out to us today.
We finna blow up.
You got the juice, Proud.
(MUSIC FADES)
I do?
Penny Proud here.
Today's episode of Growing' Up Proud
is called "Two Babies, One Diaper."
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Okay, Pride, for today's look, I'm wearing
I-got-it-from-my-Suga-Mama jeans.
-You got what from Suga Mama?
-These jeans.
Nope, I'm not having' it.
My baby girl
is not wearing' these clothes.
But Wizard Nova's paying' me to wear them,
Daddy. They even sent me a check.
Check, schmeck. If they think that
they're gonna buy my baby, then they...
(COUGHS)
Trudy!
Ugh! That is not my angle.
Delete it, basic.
Oh, no, I won't. I just paid you $50!
Then you're deleted, basic.
Next.
We're next! Me and my girls
wanna do a group selfie.
That'll be $50, right?
So, you're trying' to scam Makeup Boy?
$500, basic.
-ALL: Zang!
-Makeup Boy.
But that's okay. We got you, Makeup Boy.
Uh-uh, no, we don't, Maya.
Keep your money.
This jerk is just ripping you off.
Ooh, look who's getting spicy.
It's D-level influencer Penny Prude.
Like, are you even verified?
(ALL LAUGHING)
PENNY: (SCOFFS) Whatever.
That's right, basic. Walk away.
But what you really need to do
is sharpen up that contour
and fix that tired mug of yours. (GAGS)
I've been saying that for years.
MAKEUP BOY: Does she have her
own setting spray?
-I don't think so.
-That was a read.
MAN 1: That was stone-cold, Makeup Boy.
Basic.
(LAUGHING)
(LAUGHING IN DEEP VOICE)
Penny Proud here.
Since when are over-baked boys the
authority on the way girls should look?
-What?
-Wait a minute.
PENNY: On top of that,
he's gonna insult us and take our money?
ALL: Zang!
It's a new day, Pride.
Makeup Boy is cancelled.
(YELPS)
No, my lip gloss. My settings...
Are you kidding me?
Come back, basics. Come back.
Nubia was right. I got the power.
I got the juice.
What is the definition of an influencer?
One who has the power to make people
buy things they probably don't need
or can't afford.
And with great power comes great fear...
fear of getting cancelled by me.
And just keeping it real, people,
I kinda like it.
I know I'm not supposed to, but I do.
(LAUGHS)
Hey, you'll. What's up?
There's no room for you
at this table, Proud. Go away.
Oh, you got a problem, LaCienega?
It's just that lately
you haven't been yourself, Penny.
Not that there's anything wrong with it.
What you did to Makeup Boy
was not cool, Proud.
You ruined his life!
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
No way!
Oh, really?
(ALL GASPING)
I don't think I like you
anymore, LaCienega.
Who cares what you like, Proud?
She gonna get cancelled.
Everybody.
Hey, Pride,
I just got a traffic alert, you'll.
Guess what?
LaCienega Boulevardez... is closed.
Please seek alternate friends.
(LAUGHS MANIACALLY)
Bye...
...bye!
TRUDY: Ooh, that was
Principal Hightower calling, Oscar.
Penny's been late to school
every day this week.
-But we didn't hear that from her.
-Oh, oh-oh.
I wouldn't wanna be Principal Hightower
when Penny hears she ratted her out.
-Oscar, you need to talk to her.
-Why me?
'Cause you're the man of the house.
Oh, now I'm the man. The way I see it,
the person who always brags
about making' the most money
should be the one doing all the talking.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
It's a darn shame.
You'll scared of you'll own child.
But I'm not.
-Hey! What up, fam?
-I'll tell you "what up."
The principal called and said
you've been late every day this week.
Oh, she did, did she?
Suga Mama,
you just got that woman whacked.
SUGA MAMA: Shut up, boy.
Penny, you're grounded.
(NEIGHING)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Don't you eyeball me, girl.
(WHIPLASH)
You don't want none of this smoke.
Get on up to your room.
Say hasta la vista to Suga Mama.
Hey, Pride. It's a sad, sad day
in the Proud crib.
My Suga Mama has got the sugars.
She's gotta lose 50 pounds or else.
Help me help her, Pride.
Help me... help her.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
We're here to save you, sugar bear.
Save me? Save me where?
My boot camp. No pain, no gain.
We're Gonna get your weight down
so you can feel your toes.
-BUFFERINA: Bufferina.
-Hold her tight, Bufferina.
-Hold still...
-Let me go!
-before I crush you.
-Where you takin' me?
Dr. Payne, my good man, as you can see,
she's in denial about everything.
Except for cookies. Lots of cookies.
So, please, take care of my dear mother.
(CHUCKLES)
Hopefully, forever.
And her little dog too.
I'm gonna get you, Oscar. You...
(TIRES SCREECHING)
HIGHTOWER: Uh. Officers.
Officers, please.
Unhand me, you glorified hall monitors.
Ooh. She shouldn't have dropped
that dime on Penny.
Well, I would say let's go to class,
but Penny's gotten rid of all the
teachers, janitors, hall monitors,
the school nurse. Pretty much everybody.
Now, come on, y'all.
Homegirl is trippin' trippin'.
-We gotta do something' about this.
-You better squash that.
-You trying' to end up like LaCienega?
-Who cares what you like, Proud?
I like strawberry ice cream.
You don't like pizza? Well, I like pizza.
And you ruined Makeup Boy's life.
Hey, y'all, what's going' on?
-Everything's good, boss.
-Everything's good.
-You looking good.
-ZOEY: How about you, boss?
Nothing. Since you
got rid of Principal Hightower,
the teachers,
and everybody else up in here.
-You got a problem with that, Maya?
-Yes. I do.
You know, at least
Makeup Boy was making people look good.
-You're destroying lives, Penny.
-And don't you forget it.
Hey, I'm just kidding'. Lighten up,
Lil' Kim. It's just business.
Oh, so, I get it. You're a sellout, too.
(GASPS) Be careful, Maya,
before she drops a video on you.
Maya didn't mean it, Penny.
Did you, Maya? Tell her. Quick.
Sure, Penny.
I didn't mean it.
Glad you know what time it is, Maya.
It's boring around here.
Ooh, let's go to the movies.
Penny, there are no more movies.
You gave them all bad reviews.
All right, well, let's go to Wizneyland.
ZOEY: Nope, you closed that down, too.
Wiz?
Hey, Wiz, is that you? It's Oscar.
Oscar Proud. (LAUGHS)
Let's meet about that deal we discussed.
Hello?
(SQUEAKING)
What is it? Can't you see
I'm on the phone?
What do you mean, I'm not on the phone?
Hologram Live? How do I cut this off?
KG, let me holla at you for a second.
(SIGHS) Let's see how many
millions of followers I have today.
-(YELPS)
-(PHONE BEEPS)
(YELPS)
What is happening?
(INDISTINCT LAUGHTER)
Hightower? What're you doing' here?
Penny Proud. I've been looking for you.
I regret to inform you
that you've got detention.
Every day for the next year!
-Have a nice day.
-PENNY: What?
Hey! Don't walk away from me.
-LaCienega, who let you out of the locker?
-I did. What's up?
-It's Maya. Come on.
-Bye.
Oh! So, you wanna take her place?
A lot has changed since
I came out of the locker, Proud.
Yeah. Your reign of terror
is over, forehead.
Yeah, even I'm not scared of you anymore.
I guess you haven't checked
your Hologram lately. Have you, Penny?
Yeah, I've checked my Hologram.
-What did you do?
-GIRL: You cancelled.
You know you're not the only one
who can make a video, right, sis?
And the new number one on Maya's
sellout list,
toppling Uncle Ruckus after a record
600 weeks in the top spot... Penny Proud.
The girl that will sell anything,
including you.
And I was just sent
the video that proves it.
WIZARD: Here you go, Oscar Proud.
Something you ain't never seen before.
One big old bag of money, you'll.
(OSCAR LAUGHING)
You just made a wise investment,
Wizard, my man.
I guarantee. my daughter won't disparage
on any more of your many businesses.
WIZARD: If the Pride knew
that Penny Proud's daddy
was takin' money and Salisbury steak
under the table...
...I hate to think of the
consequences of such
an unscrupulous transaction,
You'll. The Pride? Those sheep?
They'll do whatever Penny
tells them to do. Give me my steak.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(STUDENTS LAUGHING)
(LAUGHING CONTINUES)
(MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING)
(DRAMATIC STING)
(BARKING)
-Hey, there.
-MAKEUP BOY: Miss Sophie, where are you?
-Who do you belong to?
-MAKEUP BOY: Sophie.
Miss Sophie.
Miss Sophie, where are you?
Thank you, I thought I lost her.
Penny Proud?
I don't want any trouble, Makeup Boy.
Girl, my name is Sebastian Boyle.
Look, it's all good.
Ooh. She likes you. You want her?
-You selling puppies now?
-No, sis. I'm rescuing them.
"Save the beagles"?
Yeah. They use these
poor babies to test makeup.
Isn't that right, Miss Sophie? It's awful.
Aside from kicking some butt,
I figured this was the least I could do.
Oh, yeah. That's nice.
And you know what? I owe it all to you,
Penny Proud. Thank you.
What?
You don't owe me anything.
What do you mean? Yeah, I do.
I had lost sight of who I was.
I was seduced by the juice,
and you made me see all that.
Don't let it happen to you, Penny Proud.
-Sophie.
-Yeah, too late.
Make sure to take everything.
Oscar, they're taking everything!
Not everything.
For the first time, I've won, Trudy.
I put that big old bag of money
I got from the Wizard, in the bank,
and there's nothing he can do about it.
Great, Oscar!
Wait a minute,
what bank did you put it in?
I opened a brand-new account
at the Wizard Kelly Federal Union.
I even got me a new toaster.
Wait a minute. Did I say Wizard Kelly?
(SCREAMING) No!
I can't believe this. He got me again!
Well, at least we got rid of Suga Mama.
Hello, son.
Oh, snap! It's Suga Knight
and she's swole. Jailhouse buff.
Yeah. Thanks to my homie, Dr. Payne,
I'm ready to inflict some.
Time to get rough, Puff.
(GROWLING)
(SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
PENNY: No, Suga Mama.
Look, it's my fault. I had you sent
to boot camp, and I owe you an apology.
In fact, I owe all of you an apology.
I was wrong.
I was seduced by the juice.
You hear that, Suga Mama?
Penny's been drinking too much juice.
-I hope you all can forgive me.
-Of course we forgive you, baby.
Oh, Penny, you're my grandbaby.
You can do no wrong.
But your daddy... that's another story.
(WHISTLES)
(GROWLING)
OSCAR: Let me go!
(OSCAR GRUNTING AND SCREAMING)
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)