It looks deserted.
I don't think they're there anymore.
You said this place was empty.
I thought it was.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
Just... hanging.
The house was just empty, dude,
and we were just hanging out, so...
Look, this house belongs to us.
Oh.
Why do you have so many beds?
So when friends stay over,
they have somewhere to sleep.
Can we join you?
All right, I'm about to go to school.
Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
I'll be back around
5:00. Maybe we could...
you know, get some
food or watch something.
Yeah, maybe.
This isn't forever, Agatha, I promise.
Wh-what's... what is that?
A-are you texting? Who are you texting?
- Mason.
- What?
Not Garrett?
No.
- You promise you're not...
- No, I'm not texting Garrett.
Can we just not do this again?
I don't want to play this scene.
You're not supposed
to be texting anybody.
What are you... what are
you doing contacting people?
- That's how they'll find us.
- Maybe I want to be found.
You don't mean that, right?
I was looking right at you.
What were you thinking?
I was thinking we could come
to some sort of an agreement.
Yeah?
What kind of agreement?
You can't take the bottles, okay?
I'm not gonna press any charges...
- Where have you been?
- For a run.
I don't believe you.
- I'm gonna take a shower.
- Stop.
What, Sophie?
- Take off your shorts.
- No.
- Take off your shorts now, Garrett!
- I'm not in the mood.
You've been cutting again, haven't you?
- You've been fucking cutting...
- Just leave me alone!
Do I make you unhappy?
Are you unhappy here?
Let me in.
Just tell me what happened to you.
What happened to me?
You want to know what happened to me?
I don't think you could handle it.
Breeda?
Hey.
Ow!
No! Agatha, you need to
learn how to control it!
God, you have to learn
how to control it, Agatha.
Where do you think we are?
We're not there anymore.
That was really intense.
Can we get together again?
I don't do repeats.
Yeah, it's definitely him.
The front door's unlocked.
Three bucks.
- Excuse me.
- Uh, sorry.
I've got to use the restroom.
Get off me.
He's here. We got him.
Okay. I'll be right up.
I have been here, what,
almost ten years now.
Trust needs to be
maintained on both sides,
- and we don't want anyone to...
- Leave?
... be antagonistic or have problems,
or, you know...
Are you suggesting that I have
a grudge against the institute?
That's crazy.
No, dude, no. Like, you're overthinking.