I can see why you picked this place.
It's beautiful.
It's okay.
We were never gonna stay here for long.
I love staring out at the ocean.
It's so calming.
You know I'd never
seen the ocean before?
Not as a child.
Not at the institute.
This is the first time.
I had no idea.
I love the waves.
Just staring at them...
calms me down.
Calms you down about what?
I've been thinking about how
people have different... needs...
different reasons for existing.
Being confronted with what I want,
not being what you want,
not being what someone else wants.
It just...
surprised me.
You were surprised by that?
I suppose what I'm trying to say is,
I never had a desire
to leave the institute,
disregard everything I've
learned, abandon all my friends.
I never felt the need to just
leave and take 60 people with me.
Everything you've learned.
What have you learned there, Parker?
Well, it helped me.
I felt protected by it, elevated by it.
And the institute teaches a freedom
that does not exist out here.
Can you stop calling it an institute?
It's a cult. It's a fucking cult.
You know, it's strange.
Kevin had told me to
do whatever it takes...
to get you and bring you back.
"Whatever it takes," he said.
Then the other night, you just...
you just waltz in as if
it's another ordinary day.
"Whatever it takes." Sometimes
I wonder what that means.
He was probably giving
you permission to kill me.
So at what point did you
decide to leave the program?
I'd be dead if I
hadn't left the program.
Why are you being so
dramatic and negative?
Honestly, I don't understand...
No, you don't understand, all right?
I would've slit my own fucking throat
if I'd be there any longer, all right?
Instead you're what?
What are you?
Where are you? Out here you're nothing.
In LA, you're going nowhere.
You have no one.
So why did you do this?
If you're here to take me back,
or reprogram me or whatever it is, man,
just don't-don't drag it.
Just-just kill me.
Drag what out?
Why-why do you think
someone wants to kill you?
Did you ever hear about... Tier Four?
- It was part of the institute.
- Tier Four?
No, I don't know. What is that?
It was located in Seattle.
Only a few people knew about it.
It was supposed to be kept a secret.
Secret why?
Certain things happened in Tier Four
that didn't happen in the compound.
Did you really never hear about this?
No.
Really?
So you don't know anything
about the Russian connection,
the Chinese connection,
the deep Web stuff?
I mean, I'm assuming since you're here,
you've been chosen for
the assignment, that...
you must've known certain things.
No.
Ted Lonergan might've
had some cool ideas
about evolution and
about the idea of freedom.
All cool things.
One of the reasons why I was there.
They got fucked up along the way.
- Very fucked up.
- What are you talking about?
I don't think he intended torture,
and violence and rape...
to be the endgame.
Once that door was open,
once that possibility was tasted,
it was impossible to shut that door.
I've never seen any of
that at the institute.
And yet you took care
of the Genesis patient.
Breeda.
I mean, you saw what they did to her.
You don't consider
that a form of torture?
Uh, I wasn't a part of that. I was...
I was just a handler. I
took care of her afterwards.
And yet you were cool
with the little experiment?
Trying to see if they
can raise a follower?
I mean, I was there.
I saw what they did to
her, and it was fucked up.
Breeda's here with me now.
I'm taking care of her.
Really? She is?
I'm surprised they let that
monster out of the institute.
Or did you?
I'm gonna show you something.
She's dead.
Gwen Douglas is dead.
How?
She committed suicide.
Sorry.
Ryder's still out there, though.
You want to find him, right?
We want to reach out to everybody.
I saw him yesterday.
He wanted to run away with Agatha,
get out of California.
But for some reason, I just
don't think you want to find him.
You want to leave him alone.
I mean, if Agatha's
here and Ryder isn't,
it just makes me think
you didn't try hard enough.
You said you wanted to use this.
Where is this?
This was actually shot
in Tier Four about a year ago.
I don't understand.
Just watch.
What the fuck?
I-I can't watch that
anymore. What was that?
Why did you show that to me?
That's what happens on Tier Four.
I can't go back.
Are you gonna let me go?
I can't go back without you.
Then I want you to kill me.
She's back.
So your brother has come back
to the scene of the crime.
Did you miss him?
Ryder?
Your brother.