Who are you?
What do you want?
I was looking for someone.
The door was open. Is everything okay?
My girlfriend's gone missing.
She left. I...
I don't know.
Do you know where she went?
No.
I don't.
Do you want me to help you find her?
You know where she is.
You know where she is, don't you?
You're home now, Agatha.
You're safe.
Do you have any? I need it.
I need it. Do you have any?
Why do you need it so badly?
Why do you need the Guidance?
Guidance is the only thing
that makes the pain go away.
It's the only thing that makes me feel.
Agatha, why did you leave the compound?
Please?
Why did you... why did
you... Agatha, look at me.
- Why did you get on that bus?
- Please?
Did Logan... did he say anything
to you to influence your decision?
Please? I'll tell you everything
you need to know. Just help me.
Please?
Why would you think I know
where your girlfriend is?
That's weird.
Why have I never seen you?
Maybe you weren't looking.
They taught you how to do that,
didn't they, at the institute?
Taught me what? What institute?
How to... act normal,
fake everything.
You're the Genesis patient.
You never even knew how to be natural.
That was their goal.
You never had limits.
You don't know anything about me.
I know that you were... made...
by a committee in a lab.
Where is she?
- Yeah?
- Hey.
Do you want to come out
and meet some of my friends?
Just casual.
Um, not really.
Just for a second?
Please? They think you're hot!
Yeah. If they only knew...
Yeah.
That's what I said.
Um, let me clean up, okay?
Okay.
So none of you...
called the police or
anything like that, right?
No. No, nothing like that.
Not even Ryder?
Ryder isn't like that, Parker.
Why isn't he like that?
Because he's afraid of
what you're capable of.
He shouldn't be afraid.
I hate that he's afraid.
I hate it too.
And that's why we need
to get him back, right?
Yeah.
We never should've left.
It wasn't your fault.
It wasn't your fault. It was Logan.
How would I know where
your girlfriend is...
if I don't even know you?
No, we haven't met,
but I know what you...
Fuck!
Hey. What's up?
Hey. You're Kylie's cousin, right?
Yeah. Hey.
And I'm Jessica. I'm her friend.
Jessica.
Okay.
I'm on the show with Kylie.
We just wrapped season two.
"Show"?
What show? You guys are
on a show together or...
You didn't know Kylie stars on a show?
Actually, no, I actually do. Um...
Th-the... what's it called again?
I think I've seen it before. It's...
It's called Band Together.
- Just a group of girls.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. That show.
For some reason, I thought that...
you were talking about
something else, so I... yeah.
Is this, like, a...
is this, like, a joke? Are you serious?
Um...
I've just been...
I've been gone for a while, and, uh...
I've actually been out of the
country for a long time, and...
I'm just trying to acclimate myself.
A little piece of advice?
You should make sure
you're completely acclimated
before you start
conversations like this.
It's super awkward, and it'll
save you a ton of embarrassment.
I'm all right.
We should get out of here.
I got a couple friends,
they're throwing a party.
It'll be fun.
Yeah.
Come on.
You'll dig this place, I think.
It's on the beach, in Malibu.
Malibu? Really?
That's right.
It'll be fun.
Yeah.
I'm sure it'll be a lot of fun.