So we finally get to
record your brother.
You've, um, finally allowed
us to do this, Parker.
Yes, yes. This is Ryder,
my younger brother.
Half brother. We have different dads.
And how did you come to be with us...
here at the institute, Ryder?
Uh...
Frankly, the women are extremely hot.
Meaning? What does this mean?
Meaning, I introduced
him to a few girls online,
and, uh... he never really
got the entire vibe of...
of what really happened
here at the institute,
but I introduced him to
Sandy and Ebra after that.
- Oh, right. Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay.
- And, yeah...
and that was six months ago,
and he hopped on a plane, and...
now we're together again.
It's cool.
How long have you been
here at the institute?
Like three years.
Maybe three and a half.
I met this guy online.
Well, he reached out to me.
And who was that?
Uh, Jeff Calloway.
He reached out to me, and
then he left a year later.
Uh, do you know why Jeff
Calloway left the institute?
No, actually. Uh, I have no idea.
But... he's who got me here.
And how did he do that?
He made me fall in love with him.
When did you get here?
About two and a half years ago.
And how did you find yourself here?
- I was invited.
- By who?
- Agatha.
- Oh, right. Um...
And how did you meet Agatha?
She reached out to me online randomly,
and she had seen my Instagram
and thought I was cute, I guess.
And then what happened?
Then I kind of liked her,
from, you know, what I could see,
and as we talked,
I really started liking her.
And then she actually invited me...
to meet her in Olympia.
So, um, how are you
feeling today, Mason?
Uh, I'm a little tired.
- Yeah? Why?
- That party. The gathering.
Last night got kind of crazy.
I did some things that I've
never done before but...
always wanted to try, I guess.
It was fun. I... really got off.
We are updating our video
files with everyone here
and just want to confirm how
you arrived at the institute,
which was, um, five years ago, right?
Yeah. I met a member here online.
And that member was?
Logan Conrad.
I, uh, reached out to
him on his Instagram.
I thought he was really hot, and, um...
I mean, I never knew this place
existed when he got back to me.
You're looking a little
scruffy there, Logan.
How are you doing?
Good. I'm doing good.
So I hear you're doing a
final update on everyone.
Did Ted freak out about something?
Why don't you just tell them
what you're really looking for?
Why don't you just tell them?
I mean, why are you so concerned
if they made it this far?
Well, we do tell them ultimately.
I mean, we just look for
any deviations, any cracks.
I mean, it's just a way
of monitoring things.
Well, I remember...
when I first got here.
You know, living in
an alternative world,
saying "fuck you" to the status quo,
all the drugs paid for...
I mean, who doesn't like that?
And it doesn't hurt that
everyone here is fucking hot.
Ryder, do you miss your home?
Um...
I'd probably say no.
Yeah, no, the answer's no.
Um... are you beginning
to understand fully
what is expected of you here,
and are you okay with it?
Has it been okay so far?
Yeah. I mean, you guys
give me a place to live...
here at the institute, and...
in return, I give you my commitment
to explore my personal freedom and,
um, maximize my natural potential.
Uh, do you understand
what it means exactly by...
"exploring your personal freedom"?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think I'm beginning to.
Would you say you're happy here, Logan?
Really? You're really asking me that?
Well, yeah, I mean...
Look, you had that scene
at the "Come Into Spring"
party two months ago,
- and people...
- I took too much Guidance.
I freaked out. It happens.
Well, we're only asking
because, as a senior member,
you've been here, what,
almost ten years now,
um, that a certain amount of trust
needs to be maintained on both sides,
and we don't want anyone to...
What, are you...
... be antagonistic or have problems...
or, you know...
Are you suggesting that I have
a grudge against the institute?
That's crazy.
No, dude, no. Like,
you're overthinking it.
I feel at home at the institute,
'cause... I feel like
there are no labels to
a person's sexuality.
So you don't feel uncomfortable
that you have been,
now after five years,
with both men and women, both
genders, here at the institute?
I feel more comfortable.
Would you say you've
excelled in these sessions?
Definitely, yeah.
These are samples of a
new version of Guidance
that we have been developing here
at the institute in the last year.
We've been doing test studies
with subjects not affiliated
with the institute,
and now we want to try
it on a group of members
who have been selected at random.
We would never do anything
to put you at risk,
and if you're uncomfortable
continuing with any of this,
please tell me.
What do I do with it?
Well, unlike the original Guidance,
this can be inhaled by spray
or applied topically on
or near mucous membranes,
or you can drink it.
Um, you choose how to administer it.
Can-can I do more?
Mason?
You didn't want Ryder
in the room anymore.
Why?
I just feel that...
using the Guidance this
early in his teaching
could be damaging for long-term.
'Cause when I first
got to the institute,
I took Guidance almost
immediately, and...
I was not prepared for it.
I just think that at the beginning,
there's so much information
that you're taking in.
I think that should be
enough at the beginning,
and I think later,
if he wants to expand his
potential for feeling and thought,
then he should take the
Guidance, because it does do that,
but I think he needs
to be more mature first.
Look, in just two years,
you've really proved yourself to be
one of the most loyal members here,
and your commitment to the
institute has been really remarkable,
and especially for
someone so young. Um...
- Thank you.
- But there is just the faint idea
that there are things
about the institute
that you, uh, you would
like to see changed,
and that's why, I don't know,
it makes me a little bit ambivalent
when you discuss how
the Guidance should be...
- administered to your brother.
- No. That is not my intention at all.
- I'm very sorry.
- I want you to calm down.
- This is not... it's not a big deal.
- Okay.
I feel that you're really tense.
Just calm down about it.
Garrett?
Garrett.
Yeah?
Go ahead.
It's okay.
You can do it.
What would happen to you
when you took the Guidance?
I would just freak out, and it
was a really terrifying experience,
and it didn't do anything that
my teachers told me that it would.
It was affecting my work here.
- I was anxious all the time.
- Uh, uh... Parker,
would you like to see Breeda again?
What-what do you mean see her again?
I'm one of the main
members taking care of her.
Uh, yeah, but how would you
feel if you never saw her again?
How would I feel? I...
What are you saying?
Well, this is just a test, Parker.
We want to see how Guidance affects
certain members of the community, and...
Actually we did choose you to
be one of the test subjects.
It wasn't random at all.
I'm just... I don't know what
this has to do with Breeda.
Well, if you test the Guidance,
we'll let you see her again.
And if you don't, uh,
we've talked about it,
and we might just take you
off the Genesis project.
Is this for real?
How does that feel, Garrett?
It feels fucking great.
Agatha?
Could you, um, pour yourself
a large glass of the vodka?
Uh, no. Can you pour
yourself a little bit more?
Uh, can you put it up to... to the brim?
That's good. That's good.
Um, now can you please
drink the entire glass?
Could you please pour
yourself another glass?
I feel scared.
Take the Guidance, and you won't.
I just... I really want
to see Breeda again.
Take the Guidance.
You should be feeling it immediately.
I, uh... okay.
How long does this last?
Well, are you feeling it yet?
I think so.
If I do more, can I see Breeda?
Agatha, can you hear us?
Yeah.
- You can?
- Yeah.
Are you okay?
I'm feeling good.
You don't feel sick or
anything from the vodka?
No.
You drank a very large
quantity of vodka very quickly.
I feel fine.
Logan, can you, um,
lift Agatha up and
place her on the desk?
Garrett? Come on. Garrett?
Yeah?
Um...
Can you, um,
make an incision just
below your left nipple?
There you go.
Lift Agatha's face up by her chin.
With your other hand,
I want you to slap her
hard across the face.
Agatha, how did that feel?
I want him to fuck me.
But what if he doesn't?
What would you do?
If he rejects you, what would you do?
Don't let go, Agatha.
Keep choking him. Don't let go.
- What are you feeling?
- Powerful. Feel in control.
Do you feel like you're hurting him?
Do you feel like it's too much?
No.
Parker...
- Why did you make me do this?
- Parker, come on.
Parker, come on.
- I knew it wouldn't work!
- Parker.
- Fuck you! Fuck you!
- Deep breaths. Deep breaths!
Parker? Parker?
Hold him down. Bring
her in. Bring her in now.
Breeda! Breeda!
What should I do?
Well, what you always do:
whatever you want.