Agatha. Agatha!
They're looking for you.
I think they're from the institute.
What are you gonna do
if you find everybody?
I'm going to give them back what
Logan took away... their freedom.
You can't lock me up like that, Parker.
You were supposed to be watching her.
She was still here an hour
ago when I checked in on her.
She'll be back.
The problem is what she
does when she's gone.
Who is that?
Just a person that I
didn't think needed me.
We need to do things differently here.
You can't tell me what to do anymore.
- You talked to Logan?
- Yeah.
Are you... are you gonna see him?
I think so. I... But...
But what?
What if it's a trap?
- Hey.
Um,
I'm going out for a bit.
Where are you going?
I'm just gonna go meet
a friend, you know,
one of those people that called me.
Are you gonna come back?
Yeah. Yeah. Um...
But if I don't, just...
don't get anyone else
involved, all right?
Can you promise me that?
If I don't come back, just let it go.
Don't call the police, okay?
I'm gonna need a little more than that.
Did your parents ever...
mention anything about me?
Like, what happened to me
or where I was for ten years?
No. I mean,
it was something that
wasn't really mentioned.
We all knew you were gone, but...
So... so then there's
no mention at all...
of the Lonergan Institute?
I was just 15, all right?
I was fucked up, and...
I met these really
interesting people, and, um...
and I lived with them
for ten years, and now...
now I'm back.
I was surprised to hear back from you.
Yeah. Everybody's been reaching out.
I... I need to explain... everything.
Yeah. What happened, man?
Why did you abandon us?
First off, it was part
of the arrangement.
I get everybody out of Lonergan,
you guys disappear in LA,
and there's people out here
who are willing to help you out,
but you take it from there.
- Yeah, and that's fine...
- And that's part of the arrangement,
all right? I wouldn't
be in touch with you.
I want to explain to you what happened.
What did you think would happen?
You abandoned us!
Agatha and I are hiding
out in a shitty hotel.
Hey.
Where's Mason? Did you find him?
- Where was he? Is he okay?
- He's fine.
He's better now.
- He's fine?
- Calm down.
He's fucking fine?
He was breaking down and wasted...
- Look, you've got to calm down, okay?
- ... two days ago.
It's gonna be okay.
- Everything is gonna be okay.
- Oh, my God.
Fuck you, Garrett.
I'm hiding out in a fucking motel,
and everything is gonna be okay?
You disappeared! We're
all fucking doomed!
Look, you found me, Agatha.
You brought me in to the institute.
If I'm trying to help
you, why are you so angry?
I was just doing what I was told.
- But you picked me.
- No, I didn't pick you.
The institute picked you.
They have a type, and you fit the type.
You were living in some shit town,
with some fucking shit family
- who does not give a fuck...
- Really? Really?
- ... where you end up.
- You brought me to Olympia
because I fit a fucking type? Really?
No, I picked you because
I'd fallen in love with you.
Well, this is not about
the institute anymore.
I'm not here because of the institute,
I'm here because of us.
- Our connection.
- Our connection?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, what fucking connection?
We don't have a connection.
You're with that little girl,
and I'm with Ryder, and we
have no fucking connection.
Ryder is a boy. He's all about control.
He doesn't care about sex.
He doesn't care about love.
Yes, he does care about
love, because he loves me.
And I need him. I need that.
Don't you want to be touched again?
Don't you want to be worshipped?
Don't you want to surrender again?
Where did you get that?
You're so beautiful.
Yeah, I understand that man, but...
half the people on that bus
had no idea what you were doing.
There's people on there that thought
they were going to a
fucking supermarket,
and we all ended up on a beach...
- in Los Angeles.
- Everybody on that bus...
... had been warned.
You knew what was happening.
You knew what was happening,
Garrett knew what was happening,
all of them knew what was happening.
But they didn't.
You didn't tell everyone, man.
You needed to tell everyone.
There's people on that bus that don't
have any memories of the outside world.
I risked my life to save you guys.
Do you understand that I
risked my life for that?
Gwen Douglas killed herself.
Did you hear that?
Yeah, I heard.
A week after we got here,
she took her own life.
Maybe the arrangement
wasn't working out for her.
No, Ryder.
Gwen just couldn't take
the idea of going back.
Why did you avoid everybody's calls?
Because, man. Because I lost control.
You mean you got caught up.
You got strung the fuck out.
I don't think you fully knew
what was going on in the institute.
I knew what I saw. I
know what you told me.
Yeah, but you don't know what
was going on in House Seven,
or what was happening
on Tier Four in Seattle.
They were fucking disappearing people.
Do you understand?
Yeah, I understand, man.
People are disappearing
every fucking day out here.
Garrett's gone, Mason's gone...
The only thing that I
can do to help anyone...
is just go away.
Go away. All right?
Go as far away as you can,
where no one will find you.
- Just go?
- Yeah.
Has that always been your
plan? Just to run away?
Until what?
They find us?
Bring us back and put us in Tier Four?
Or give us to the Russians?
Or do whatever the fuck they want?
Tell me. Has this always
been your fucking plan?
There's people out here that
don't know what the fuck to do.
That's on you, man.
Maybe-maybe we can take them down.
Yeah, maybe-maybe if-if...
if we get a lawyer,
and we go to the press,
they'll go over there
and fucking take them out.
Look, man, you abducted
us and you abandoned us,
and now we're in the most terrible
situation I could even think of...
there's people out here
trying to kill us...
and they're probably going to.
Hello?
We're gonna be checking out.
God!
Agatha!
Fuck.