I just really need to talk to somebody.
Can you meet me, please?
Logan said that we shouldn't
even be texting each other,
let alone meeting in person.
Mason?
Kennedy, I really
need someone to talk...
Agatha, I told you,
you can only call this number
in case of an emergency.
There's someone here.
I know it was my idea to bring Breeda.
Out of her environment, yes, I
know that she's more aggressive.
Logan? Logan?
Logan.
Did you sleep well last night?
I think we should get out of here.
You mean, like, for breakfast?
No. I mean out of this
fucking place. Out of L.A.
And why would we do that?
I know you think I'm paranoid,
but they have found us.
So say we leave, Agatha.
Say we go somewhere.
You're just gonna get paranoid again,
and then we'll move again and
again, and it'll never stop.
They will never fucking stop.
There's no proof that they've found us.
Okay. So where in the fuck is Logan?
Where's Mason? Where's Garrett?
They're all fucking gone, Ryder.
Logan hasn't responded
to a soul in months.
Mason's probably off on a bender, and...
yeah, I guess it's pretty fucking
weird Garrett hasn't responded...
especially to you.
Are you listening to
me? He's fucking gone.
Probably didn't want to deal with you.
Oh, fuck you.
He went to go meet up with Mason,
and now he's just... he's fucking gone.
Wait. Why was he with Mason?
Mason texted Garrett.
He was all fucked up, he was on drugs,
and Garrett went to meet up with him,
and I haven't heard from
either of them, so...
I don't know. I'm worried.
Will, uh... will you
go check on Garrett?
Me?
- Yeah.
- Jesus, Agatha, why?
Why can't you go check on him?
I-I don't know if he
doesn't want to talk to me.
I don't know what's going on.
Can you please, please,
just go check on him for me?
Please? I'm freaking out!
I don't know what's going on! Help me!
Hello?
Garrett?
Hey, I'm a friend of
Garrett's. My name's Ryder.
He said he was gonna go meet a friend.
- Was it Mason?
- No.
It wasn't Mason.
But I know it was that bitch...
Agatha.
Well, why would he be with Agatha?
Because he's fucking her.
I came home yesterday,
and they were both here...
naked...
and they pulled me into this
fucked-up thing, and I...
So you guys were, like, all together.
That's what I fucking said.
I know he's with her right now.
I know it. I know he's with that slut.
I mean, it... it might not be...
- it could be anyone.
- I fucking love him.
Don't you get that?
And he's fucking her.
Hey, uh, can I help you with something?
Uh, does Garrett work here?
Uh, not today. He called in sick.
- I'm here though.
- Are you a friend of Garrett?
Yeah, yeah, Garrett. That's
my guy. I know Garrett.
- Why?
- I'm from Washington.
He told me to hit him
up when I'm in L.A.,
but he hasn't been returning my texts.
- I'm lost.
- Oh, wow.
Uh, well, I get off of
here in, like, an hour.
We could hang out. You know,
maybe go get something to eat.
We can probably find out why
Garrett's not texting you back.
It'd be great if you could help me.
Hit me.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
What the fuck?
Fucking crazy bitch! Fuck!
I'm fucking her, about to come,
and she fucking scratches
the shit out of me.
I just threw her off.
Just get your shit. Let's go.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, my roommates are
gone. They're not home.
It's like I never see them.
You smoke?
Cigarettes? No.
I meant weed.
Who is that?
Who?
Is that your girlfriend?
Her. That girl.
Rihanna?
Is she your friend?
Does Garrett know her?
Look, Garrett doesn't...
She's not... Wait...
Wait, where are you from again?
Washington, just outside of Olympia.
And you don't know who Rihanna is?
Do you have the same number
for Garrett that I have?
I have to let you know,
I don't have his number.
I don't even know Garrett.
- I'm sorry.
- You don't know who Garrett is?
I don't.
But I think you're really cute,
and I would love to help you.
I just don't know Garrett.
I know we work at the shop together,
but he has different shifts from me.
You think I'm cute?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Would you want to have sex with me?
Definitely.
What time do your,
uh, roommates get home?
We've got some time.
Where have you been?
Breeda?
Breeda.
Please answer me. Where have you been?
You can't just run away like that.
Walking along the beach.
Well, where were you?
Took the Metro downtown.
What were you doing down there?
Just doing what we came here to do.
I was... I was just... I
was so worried about you.
You're my responsibility. You
can't just disappear like that.
I was looking for Garrett.
Just doing my job.
Breeda, Garrett and Mason are here.
They're here. They're safe.