A YEAR AND A MONTH AGO
It's me.
It's been awhile, Martin.
-You're doing fine.
-You have to let August go.
Don't do that to my son.
Punish me.
That's what I'm doing.
Sit down.
Why?
I need to know why.
Is that because
your wife chose me?
Have you killed
them because
you couldn't hold
on to your wife?
My marriage is over.
I lost my son.
My job, my friends.
What else then?
Where is he?
Where is August?
He is no longer here.
You'll never know
whether he suffered.
Whether he was scared.
Whether he cried.
Whether his death was long
and painful.
You'll never have
a body to bury.
a grave to visit.
Shut up.
You'll live forever
in doubt.
Shut up!
Martin!
We've found August!
-No, you haven't.
-Yes, we have.
He's in the Ejborgsvej garage.
-Is August alive?
-Yes.
Can you tell me
whether he is alive or not?
Is August really alive?
Saga!
LOTSubs presents
SAGA AND MARTIN
ARE BACK!
L.O.T.S
@lotsubs
Like us on Facebook
fb.com/lotsubs
BRON II BROEN
S02E01
This ship is weird.
-Which one?
-This one.
Faxborg, this is Sund's traffic
control on channel 71.
Faxborg, Faxborg.
Call SIGN-IN S5AB.
This is Sund's traffic
calling on channel 71.
Do you read me?
-They gave me the Kullen signal.
-Try on channel 16.
Faxborg...
Warning: You've
left the fairway
and you're heading
for shallow waters.
Faxborg, Faxborg
call SIGN-IN S5AB...
The Coast Guard
is on the way.
Faxborg, you need to direct
your course immediately.
What the hell?
-What do they have on board?
-I don't know.
We need to close
the bridge.
They're going towards
Saga Norén,
Malmö police.
Kaj Lindahl
from Coast Guard.
Hello!
Hello, hello.
Do you hear me.
Do you speak Swedish?
Yes.
Saga Norén,
Malmö police.
What happened?
Hello!
-Do you know who they are?
-They have no IDs.
-Was it all good?
-It can always get better.
-Has the ship run aground?
-I don't know.
-Have you taken the math test?
-Yes.
Why do you sail when you
have other things to do?
-The school is later on.
-You have to score there.
-I can certainly do that.
-Any more complaints?
-No.
-No, alright.
-Gdansk to Turku.
-Have a pleasant trip, Faxborg.
Over and out.
He's pronounced 'Turku'
as a Dane.
Where were them
when they made contact?
They were going southward,
advancing Kullen Lighthouse.
They came from Halmstad.
-So they left the ship?
-Yes, and they left on a boat.
-They can't be traced back.
-So you guys can't help me.
Thank you.
Saga, what about the boat?
Ship, it's 12 meters long
and 4 meters wide.
-Okay, ship.
-We found five youngsters chained.
-What about the crew?
-The ship was empty.
John, I want a list
of missing persons.
Range?
Youngs from 17 to 25 years
old in the last three months.
Okay.
Beate!
Can I work with another
person apart from Christian?
We have a perfect score,
but I'm doing all the work.
-He helps me a lot.
-On what?
-Find someone at my level.
-No.
Why not?
I can rate you
on an individual basis.
And he's also learning
from you.
Teaching is your job.
In order to check
the overtime list...
-I know who they are.
-Can't you wait a bit?
Let's put it off.
The crew member
Victor Bergström
disappeared along
with two friends,
a Danish girlfriend
and her friend.
One of his friends,
Fredrik Lundblad,
was reported missing
on Saturday.
The third is
Svante Kallen.
Police was looking for them,
with no results.
They're nowhere to be found
since Friday.
The girls on the ship were
a Danish woman and her friend?
I think so.
Ok, I'll inform
their parents.
I'll go to Copenhagen
to check their last
known whereabouts.
-Why?
-I wanna prepare the inquiring.
Saga, come on.
The case is not important.
They were enchained
to a broken ship.
It's an important case.
I'm looking for Martin Rohde.
Yes, his boss
is right there.
-Saga, long time no see!
-Yes, 13 months.
-It's nice to see you again.
-I'm looking for Martin.
Yes, I know.
Come here.
When was the last time
you guys last met?
It was at August's funeral.
-Haven't you met ever since?
-No.
What do you want from him?
A ship crashed
into the bridge.
The ship had five people
enchained.
Two women
are from Denmark.
-And we have two missing persons.
-What do you want from him?
They have been kidnapped.
I want an investigation.
-If possible...
-Someone else could help you.
-Why not Martin?
-He has other tasks.
What?
He is in the group
that coordinates
the police efforts
at the European Council.
-Isn't him here?
-Yes, but...
Saga, his recovery
took a long time.
It's been a long time,
I don't know how
he's going to react.
I'm carrying on
an investigation.
I know I could've
done that differently,
but the outcome'd have
been the same.
No one is blaming you.
Not even Martin.
Why can't I see him then?
He is on that door.
-Long time no see!
-Yes, one year and one month.
Yeah.
Shall we go to the hallway?
Good to see you.
What are you doing here?
I'm investigating
a kidnapping.
Two Danes missing.
Do you have names?
I have something to help you.
Come.
-What a joy to see you again.
-Yes, that's it.
We gotta get there.
Maria Holst
and Vibecce Nielsen.
-You could have sent me e-mail.
-How?
You could've emailed me.
I wanted to visit.
-You wanted to see me?
-Yes.
Why haven't you come before?
The investigation didn't
involve Denmark back then.
The manager saw them leaving
the Mainstreet club at 3:45 AM.
Do you know where it is?
-Mainstreet Club?
-Yes.
-I don't know.
-She was along with four men.
Only three men
were chained in the ship.
Saga Norén,
Malmö police.
When?
Great, thank you.
Maria Holst has died.
So we have
a murder investigation.
-How was that with Saga?
-Fine.
She's waiting in her car.
-For you?
-Yes.
Yes, she wants me
to go to Helsingor.
Is that ok?
I don't know.
Is that what you want?
I think it's a good idea then,
Martin.
Okay.
-How is it going?
-Fine.
-Are you working hard?
-Yes.
-Are you still single?
-You're mean.
-I'm not, Saga. I'm reasonable.
We haven't seen
each other for a year.
Don't you have
anything new to tell me?
I wanna some catch up.
-I don't live with Mette anymore.
-Are you divorced?
We just don't live
together anymore.
Have you betrayed
her again?
Nope.
I'm just not good for her
and our children anymore.
We had twins, you know?
Sanne and Simon.
Yes.
-I'm living with Jakob Sandberg.
-The flower guy?
-No, that was Anton.
-How have you guys met each other?
It was in a bar
seven months ago.
-Are you living together?
-Yes.
Full time?
Yes, since last Wednesday.
-Are you guys doing fine?
-Yeah.
Good...
Nice to know.
-Christian Fischer?
-Yes.
Martin Rohde, local police.
Saga Norén, Malmø police.
We'd like to talk
about Vibecce Nielsen.
Have you seen her
leaving at 3:45 AM?
Yes.
Was she along with four guys?
-Yes.
-Do you recognize those three?
I don't. Do you know how many
guys come here every day?
The flyer says the maximum
capacity is 950 people.
Yes.
We have full house
every weekend.
-Do you recognize her?
-Yes, a girl named Vibecce?
She left to smoke a few times.
We chatted.
I think she liked me.
Why do you remember her?
The way she talked.
-Don't you remember the guys?
-Sorry, I don't like guys.
Do you have cameras
at the entrance?
No.
-Or inside the premises?
-Nope, no cameras.
There is a camera there.
-Another there.
-They're police cameras.
I'll talk to Barbara
about the issue.
No, I'll talk to John.
It's important.
Okay.
Hey, check it out.
What is that?
Let me see.
What the hell is that?
-I put it on Youtube.
-There will be only five visits.
-Can you do better?
-Of course.
-I wanna see your apps.
-Did you watch the Barcelona game?
A bit of Messi.
-You don't have any pay channels.
-Let's go.
Wait, I'll get my coat.
Wait!
Hey, why did you do that to me?
-My cell phone.
-You cellphone what?
-You're hiding it.
-No.
-Come on.
-I left it on the bench.
So what?
Maybe someone got it.
What's the problem?
Are you still wondering about
what happened here a year ago?
No, not anymore.
And you?
Yes.
Do you think
it could be forgotten?
I just think about
what I want.
You're lucky.
-Hi.
Saga told me you're back.
Couldn't you leave?
My son and my grandchildren
moved here.
-Good.
-What about you?
You know what happened,
but I'm fine.
The four are alive,
but they don't say a word.
-Maria died of what?
-Her body was sent for autopsy.
Faxborg was in Halmstad.
It was stolen during the night,
no witnesses.
-Who owns the boat?
-Ship!
-What?
-Faxborg is a ship.
More than 12
meters in height,
and width is greater
than 4 meters.
-Is that important?
-It could be.
-Is that important on this case?
-No.
Who owns the boat?
Marcus Stenberg,
he lives in Ystad.
Martin, what
have you done?
Are you really
working on that case?
I'm helping coordinate
the police efforts
at the European Council.
But they can do the same
job without me.
-Am I answering it right?
-That's right.
-I like staying here.
-I'll talk to Lilian.
Go for it.
The ship would leave in a week.
So I stayed here.
How many people
knew about that?
The crew, of course.
The control personnel
and the Port of Halmstad.
When bees see smoke, they think
it's fire then they calm down.
It is easy to steal
a ship of that size?
It was supposed to be guarded,
I don't know how they did that.
How many people are required
to sail the ship?
In theory, a single person.
-And in practice?
-A single person with knowledge.
But to start and move it out,
it needs two.
My wife...
Marcus Stenberg.
Do you like bees?
I don't know,
I just don't think about.
Albert Einstein said
that if bees disappear from earth,
we would be extinct
in four years.
Without oxygen,
we would die in four minutes.
I still don't like air.
Sorry, it was my wife.
Can we leave that for later?
Do you recognize
anyone here?
No.
Do you know why
someone would steal your ship?
I have no idea.
But I would have to...
Call my office,
they know the crew.
Talk to Linda.
They will help you.
-He lied.
-Why?
It wasn't his wife
on the phone.
Why not?
When Mette calls you,
you don't answer
saying your first and last name.
-Have you found my phone?
-No, why?
It sent a SMS.
What kind of SMS?
Let's see.
What the hell...
I WANT TO FUCK
AMANDA
Here's your phone.
-How many people got the SMS?
-All your contacts.
What the fuck!
It was just a joke.
See you tomorrow,
loser.
We had the feeling
that they were about to wake up.
Nothing is absolute.
They are weak and confused.
Why?
They were dehydrated,
hypothermic,
and had traces
of lysergic acid in their blood.
-A LSD predecessor?
-I don't know what they took.
It was like a combination
between drug
and external influences.
They're talking about
lights and noises.
It's little crazy.
We need to talk to them.
Lundblad is still
unconscious.
-Kallen is having a high fever.
-So we'll talk to the other two.
Saga Norén,
Malmö police.
Can you tell us
what happened?
Vibecce, could you
say what happened?
Lights...
Flashing...
Lights flashing.
Try again.
A fox and...
A fox...
Saga, that is enough.
Have you left
Mainstreet with someone?
Do you remember
who was that?
-Maria.
-No, it was a man.
-Where is Maria?
-She's fine. Maria's doing fine.
She's in the next room
and she's talking.
What about the bar?
With whom have
you left the place?
It flashes...
Yes, it flashes?
Come on.
You have to explain it better.
What happened?
Thank you,
that's enough.
Come on.
-We didn't get a lot from them.
-Nope.
They're disoriented.
They can't remember anything.
Do you really believe
they were abducted by aliens?
Wait, I'll have coffee.
Why do you laugh?
The alien theory
is a joke, right?
Yes, it is, but it seems
that you didn't find it funny.
-Have noticed that?
-Yes.
It's nice to work
with you again, Saga.
It feels the same.
-I mean it.
-Me too.
You still treat me
the same way as before.
How else could I treat you?
Many people changed
after August's death.
It's because of you
we're here today.
If you hadn't shot me,
I'd have killed Jens.
I know.
Hey, come on!
-What is happening?
-Hurry.
Watch out.
What is happening?
Victor!
Calm down!
Calm down,
let's solve it peacefully.
Okay?
There're hostages,
we need extra force here.
-Release Anne-Louise first.
-No.
Release Anne-Louise now!
Ok, go away, go away
Victor, are you listening?
Release Anne-Louise
and then talk.
-Put the scissors down.
-No.
-What do you want?
-I want to leave here.
Okay, great.
First release
Anne-Louise.
Come on!
No, no.
I want to leave here.
I'll handcuff myself,
and then we leave, right?
-Martin, what is that?
-I'm harmless, see?
-No.
-Let her go and take me.
I'm coming, Victor.
Look at me. Martin.
Release Anne-Louise
and take me. Let her go.
Do you want to see
Maria, right?
Yes.
Release her now,
and you will see Maria.
Release Anne-Louise now!
-Do you know Maria?
-Turn around.
Do you know Maria?
She's dead!
Sorry, dammit!
He changed places
with the hostage?
I couldn't intervene.
Avoid him,
unless you want to.
-What did Hans say to you?
-He doesn't want our partnership.
-Why have you changed places?
-It was a good idea.
-It was a bad and dangerous one.
-I am well trained.
Not with your hands chained.
That's okay.
-Do you want a ride?
-No, thank you.
I think I'll take the train.
Say hello to Jakob.
-He doesn't know who you are.
-Greet him anyway.
Axel?
-Daddy, it's me.
-Are you coming home?
-Not yet.
-Why not
-Tina wanted me to stay.
You left,
went to school...
-And then just disappeared.
-Just for a few hours.
-See you at eleven o'clock?
-Yeah.
Faxborg crashed into
Öresund bridge this morning.
It happened
when traffic control
lost contact with the ship.
The ship didn't have
any captains or crew inside.
Five youngsters
were on board.
They are under treatment
at the University Hospital.
The police haven't said
a word on the matter.
Hi.
I thought you wouldn't
make it tonight.
I'm staying
with Tina on the stable.
-You don't talk much.
-Nope.
Don't you think
it could help?
You know it takes time.
It's a process.
I met Saga today.
-Saga Norén?
-Yes.
How was that?
A few hours with her
were more useful
than a year with you.
Then, continue with her.
I will.
And we're done here.
Okay.
It's over for today.
See you next week.
His trauma brought
serious consequences.
But he would never allow
anything bad to happen to her.
The only person he would allow
something bad is to himself.
-Hi.
You're here!
Nikolaj!
Your father is here.
Where are the others?
Carl and Johanne
are playing tennis.
I have to take them
in 45 minutes.
-Hi.
-How are you, buddy?
-I'm cooking with Anna-Dea.
-What are you cooking?
-Spaghetti.
Spaghetti!
-Hi.
-Are you staying for supper?
I can't.
I just wanted to talk to Mette.
Okay.
Come, let's continue then.
-Bye, buddy.
-Bye.
I won't attend tomorrow's
couples therapy.
How should I interpret this?
-Are you giving up?
-You know what I want.
-Don't you want to get back?
-Not this way.
-I don't want therapy anymore.
-It helped you a lot.
-Helped?
-Yes, of course.
Can't you see?
I've only learned to lie
to myself and to other people.
I see no change.
I wanna move on.
And what are you
going to do?
Lillian put me with Saga.
I'm back to Homicides.
I want you
to give me a break.
Martin, shit.
I'm waiting for your recovery
and I'm tired.
I know.
Hey!
-How are doing?
-Fine, what are you doing?
Unpacking my stuff.
-I don't want those books there.
-Where, then?
You can leave them
in the box.
We dwell together and you want
to just unpack your stuff?
No, just continue.
-Are you working tonight?
-No.
-Wanna do something?
-Why?
You decide.
Okay.
I have a co-worker
from Denmark.
-Were you thinking about him?
-Yes.
-When we fucked?
-Not, it was after the sex.
Do you think about others
when we have sex?
No, you?
-No, never.
-Okay, fine.
-Hey man. How are you?
-I'm fine, thanks.
-Any messages for me?
-No, sorry.
-What are you doing?
-Reading.
"Relationship
competence"?
"Emotions
and social relations."
"Codes for a better
relationship."
-Where did you get them?
-Library.
Why, Saga?
-I want to be good at it.
-Like living together?
In having
a romantic relationship.
You are good at that one.
-How can you tell?
-I don't know, I just feel.
This is my first one.
Let's go to bed.
Check it out.
"The discovery of the need
to be loved..."
-Why are you that early?
-I came to see you.
Okay.
I did quit therapy.
Niels said nothing
about that.
That's because he thinks
I can't decide anything.
You can't.
We have a deal.
I know what I want.
I wanna talk to Jens in prison.
It's out of question.
You know I'm not living
with my family for a year now.
Mette has a maid.
I need to move on.
And that doesn't work.
So you're
investigating a murder.
We will solve
an issue at a time.
I wanna see him in his cell,
you know, arrested and locked up.
-You know he's already there.
-It's not enough.
Niels has to agree
or it's a no go.
Okay.
None of the parents know
why the youngsters disappeared.
Marcus Stenberg seems innocent.
Look carefully.
So he didn't have any
contact with the lost ones?
Nope.
However, we will continue
to investigate him.
-Have you obtained the videos?
-No, they are delaying it.
-You know it's important.
-Yes.
-It's Martin.
-I've talked to Niels.
He's always here.
We'll perform periodic
assessments,
and you'll have to behave
the way he wants you to.
-Can I see Jens?
-At 2 P.M.
Has he made any demands?
No, the director said that he
promptly accepted the offer.
Really?
At 2 P.M., ok?
I'm allowed
to see Jens.
Jens, the guy
who killed your son?
-Yes.
-Why?
Something good could
come out
from a meeting between
victim and perpetrator.
It only has positive effects when
the aggressor wants redemption.
-It doesn't apply to Jens.
-Of course not.
No.
Why do you want
to see him, then?
I think about him all the time.
It's spinning in my head.
-Understood?
-No.
I wanna see if he is human.
Do you know what I mean?
Is a bad idea.
I have to go.
I'm serious.
It's a really bad idea.
-What do you want to show us?
-Take it.
Why?
Wait, you film it.
Here.
What the hell are you doing?
Put out the fire!
Put out!
Help me! Put it out, Albin!
Put out the fire.
I can't.
It's locked!
The extinguisher is locked.
Don't go anywhere.
The extinguisher is locked!
Stop filming
and help me!
Excuse!
Is Linus Svensson here?
I'm Niklas, his brother.
Ok, so he doesn't
have any parents?
No, just me.
How is he?
He suffered 1st and
2nd degree burns.
-That's good, right?
-It'll hurt for awhile.
But he'll not need
any surgeries.
Come, I will show you
where he is
Sorry.
Saga, you have a guest.
Hi.
Saga Norén,
Malmö police.
Axel Mollberg,
I have everything filmed.
-What was time then?
-8:30 AM.
Do you know whether he was
heading towards Sweden or Denmark?
No, I was there
filming my daughter.
-Shit.
-John!
Saga!
I need to show
this video to John.
Saga, you need
to come over now!
-No, I have some film...
-You need to come over now!
Shaw we go in?
He wanna see you, right?
I'm doing that because
it's something you believe.
-Want to proceed?
-Yes, I do.
-Saga, I was going to call you.
-Come to the hospital.
-Two of them have died.
-Let me tell you...
You need to come
to the hospital.
They died of aggressive
pneumonic plague.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Severe pneumonia
caused by bacteria.
We are isolated.
Shit, I went to see my children.
Am I infected?
Yes, pneumonic plague.
Someone deliberately
infected them.
Someone wants to create
a plague epidemic.
L.O.T.S
fb.com/lotsubs
@lotsubs