The pin on the jacket.
They claim it, leave a symbol.
Negative human impact
on the environment - hence the symbol.
So a pathos-driven
eco-terrorism of sorts?
-Murderers! You're killing people!
-I won't leave you.
I can't do this.
I have Linus to think of.
Nobody's leaving, OK?
The police, please.
-The cops came.
-How did they find us?
That's what we'd like to know.
Five more stores have found amulets.
Two of them have CCTV.
Print out
the sharpest image you can get.
-See you tomorrow, loser.
-Point them out to me.
Do we understand each other?
I want to see Jens in prison. I need
to see that he's in there - locked up.
-I got a ten on my test.
-You must be happy.
Do I look happy?
You can buy them for me.
You're my teacher after all.
Your math teacher called.
-Pulling night shifts now?
-I can't go home.
-I thought I'd crash here.
-Sure, why not?
That's five gallons of gas. We just
got hold of five thousand gallons.
EPISODE 3
What the hell...?
There's a tanker standing here.
-I'm going to check it out.
-Copy that.
Can we go to the harbor?
We won't get close
and there's little left to examine.
-Fatalities?
-Unknown, but four people are missing.
-Voytek Rosenau had this in his pocket.
-Who is Voytek Rosenau?
Polish truck driver. He was assaulted
last night and his tanker got jacked.
-What do we know?
-No more than I told you on the phone.
I bet this time
it's about car pollution.
I don't know. They'll probably
upload a video about it.
The pictures of the girl from the store.
Saga? Ölanders Livs -
no toad was found in the meat section.
-Did you look hard?
-No, just under the first piece.
But it might be in the cracks!
There were three of us.
We looked through everything.
-We found nothing.
-You missed it.
We went through it twice.
We did not miss it.
-You must have!
-Except we didn't.
The driver is out of surgery.
The doctors say we can question him.
-Rasmus!
-You want me to come with?
I've been involved in questionings
in my previous cases, so...
Oh. Yeah, no.
See if you can identify her.
These are pictures from stores
with golden toads.
The man who died.
I'm sure you've read about it.
I know it's extremely short notice.
All you have to do is show up,
and we'll take care of the rest.
That's great.
See you tomorrow, then. Thank you!
-We booked her?
-Not sure yet. She'll be here tomorrow.
-And the programs?
-Worst case, we use the old ones.
Put a leaflet in
when we know she's a yes.
-Do I give her clearance?
-Yes.
And get some pictures of her
we can use. That'd be all, Dharma.
-Remember to call Alexander.
-Right.
Hi, honey. You sure are
one busy birthday girl.
I know, I'm sorry I left
before you woke.
Maybe you can prepare the dinner party
tonight if I mail you what to do?
-Will you be late?
-I hope not.
-Should we cancel?
-No, I want my dinner party and gifts!
Yeah...
I've got to go. I'll see you tonight.
There's just one more thing...
Hey! What's this?
The explosion woke me,
but I didn't dare to call you.
You were the ones who did it, right?
-Did anyone die?
-I don't know, I wasn't there.
I hope not.
-Thanks.
-How's it going?
How it's going? Well, I'm thinking
this can't be this girl's first rodeo.
So I'm going through police footage
from a bunch of protests.
-You need help?
-It's probably not worth it.
Nazi lieutenant over there
is just going to get on my ass.
Voytek, the truck driver,
said two of his assailants were women.
So two of the animals in the video
are probably women.
-How's the search?
-Great. Got an instant match.
Why didn't you call? Who is it?
It was a joke. Look at this picture,
it could be fucking anyone.
-Right...?
-Right, so... No, no match yet.
OK...
-Saga doesn't get irony.
-I've noticed.
But I sure do. So why don't you
stop taking the piss?
Sure thing.
-Beate?
-Yes.
-May I have a word?
-Sure.
Please have a seat.
-I need to ask you something.
-Yes?
Are you having
a sexual relationship with a student?
I... I can explain.
-Beate...
-She is over eighteen.
And it hasn't affected
the school in any way.
Everything has been going on
outside of school.
That's irrelevant.
You're one of my best teachers.
-But rules are rules.
-Right.
I need to ask you to pack up your things
and leave the premises.
Right away.
-You happy now?
-What?
-A fucking pair of shoes, Laura?
-I tried to call and apologize.
-You get my dad involved...
-You go to the principal?
My career down the drain
for a pair of shoes!
You're sick.
I hope you like living alone,
because no one could ever stand you.
What did you do?
What the hell did you do?
You made a mistake,
she made a bigger one...
-She'll think I did it!
-It can't be that bad.
-I'll call the school and explain...
-Don't do anything!
You've already outed me
as a total bitch.
-Hi.
-Hi? What are you doing here?
-Is Lene still on sick leave?
-Yes.
-I can take her job.
-But it's full time. You've got school.
I think I'm dropping out.
No, don't.
Not for a reception-desk temp job.
I'm taking a break, anyway.
Top students don't take gap years.
What did you get yourself into?
Do I get the job or not?
-You know how everything works?
-If not, I'll ask someone.
-I've got to run. I'll see you later.
-Sure thing.
-I was wondering if you'd come.
-Why haven't you gone in?
-They're about to give him a bath.
-OK. You want to go for a smoke?
-How are things going with you?
-Good.
-And with you?
-They're going.
-Need me to lend you more money?
-No.
-What happened at the harbor?
-I know, that was sick.
-I didn't know it was part of the plan.
-It was Mads' idea.
-Have you heard what they thought?
-Not yet.
But I think
they should be quite pleased.
OK. We're shooting a video later.
I'll pick up Kattis when we're done here.
Which one are you?
You don't know? Take a guess.
-The hare?
-The fox.
Right, of course.
-What are you checking?
-If it's the same people in both videos.
-You think there are more of them?
-Could be.
These groups tend to work in cells.
The pig is definitely the same guy.
The scar on the wrist.
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
We'll be right there. Bye.
That's the spot.
Come on!
Are you and Pernille having sex?
No. What makes you think that?
You spend a lot of time together
and she's always touching you.
-She does?
-Yes.
Well, we're not.
Are you and Mette still having sex
even though you're separated?
No. It's been a long time.
-So who are you having sex with?
-No one.
How do you cope? You used to
have sex with people all the time.
That's one good thing about living
with someone. Sex is easy to come by.
Jakob is good at having sex.
He does as I say.
Well, that's great. Congratulations.
Thank you. Are you?
-Am I good at sex?
-Yes?
Why would you possibly
need to know that?
-We're talking about it.
-No, you are.
-Yes?
-And I think you should stop.
OK.
-But if...
-Saga.
-It's this one.
-What about it?
We don't throw our boxes here,
and it belongs to none of our suppliers.
We know... No, don't!
You provided a list.
Since it's apples,
I thought I should call.
"Utile Frukt AB."
It went out to Sherens Livs
in Möllevången, Malmö.
Thank you.
-Where are you going?
-Just heading out. Get some air.
Hi. Rasmus Larsson, Malmö Police...
Come on, hurry up!
-Hello?
-You on your way?
-Why not?
- I told you, I've got Linus.
-We told you no one gets out.
You needed me in the beginning.
I've done my part.
-Three things, that's enough.
-So you're not coming?
No.
Hi! I hope I am interrupting.
Happy birthday! Oh, little sis.
-Are you stressed?
-I'm chasing a new keynote speaker.
The guy we got ruined my birthday
by getting poisoned and dying.
-People are so rude.
-I'll have to cancel our lunch.
No, Caroline, you don't have to.
You've got people under you.
Delegate some of this stuff,
and take an hour off.
All right, fine. Two minutes.
Two.
-What did Alexander do for you?
-I left before he woke.
-Any morning sex, at least?
-Stop it.
Isn't your birthday
the one day you get physical?
-It is not!
-When did you last have sex?
If you need to think about it,
it was too long ago.
-I know exactly what to get you.
-Not another sex toy.
What? It made the unwrapping of your
Christmas gifts all the more exciting.
Seriously... You!
-What's up with you?
-A cop rang on her door.
-A cop?
-Easy now.
Kattis, go make yourself a cup of tea.
Niklas isn't coming,
because of his fucking kid brother.
OK, I'll send someone to talk to him.
In the meantime, you talk to her.
OK.
Here.
Thanks.
-So he just found you?
-Yes.
You know what we've done.
And the police just send one guy?
Who just knocks on your door?
-Well, I can't help if you think...
-Something you want to tell me?
-No.
-What's that?
-You remember who bought this?
-The box?
-It had apples in it.
-No idea, we get a ton of those.
-You sell a lot of whole boxes?
-No, but it happens.
-I sold one last week.
-To whom?
Young guy, my age. Niklas, I think.
-You know him?
-No, but he answered his phone in here.
Brown hair, average height,
thin, blue eyes.
-OK. Is that all?
-He's Swedish, the name's Niklas.
-Start a search around Mads Nielsen.
-And that activist, Astrid.
-Mads and Astrid know each other.
-And Astrid Simonsen.
-Get Rasmus to help you.
-He took off.
-Where to?
-Don't know.
OK.
Niklas. Who's this?
OK, I'll be down.
Who are you? What's this?
Great. Thanks for letting me know. Bye.
-Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
-It's me. Pernille.
It could be a Niklas Svensson, age 23.
Appears alongside Astrid and Mads.
Studied biochemistry, but dropped out.
He's a lab technician
at Medisonus in Copenhagen.
They say he's been home
with his younger brother.
-Where is home?
-Two secs.
Do we understand each other?
What the fuck is this?
It happens around here
with these nice cars.
For fuck's sake...
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
This is my colleague Martin Rohde.
-Is Niklas home?
-No.
-Where is he?
-Out.
-When will he be back?
-Dunno.
We need to come inside.
-You live here with your brother?
-Yes.
-Where are your parents?
-Dead.
Niklas! The police are here! Run!
Niklas!
Fuck... Saga!
He's running down the stairs!
Goddamn it!
-Saga?
-In here.
-Where's the kid?
-He was gone when I came back.
-Did you issue a BOLO?
-Not to be picked up, surveillance only.
We specialize in third-world
vaccines and maladies.
We focus our research on malaria, AIDS,
different fever illnesses... This way.
Did Niklas Svensson
have access to palytoxin here?
Is that what they used
in the poisonings?
-Just answer the question.
-Please, have a seat.
We stock biochemical substances
for reference, among them palytoxin.
-Could Niklas Svensson access them?
-It's not entirely implausible.
-Why can't you just say yes?
-Beg your pardon?
You're being evasive.
Why can't you just say yes?
We have procedures in place
for access to biochemical substances.
I've not yet been able to look into
whether Niklas signed out anything.
We'll let you know when we do.
Could he have gotten
the plague contagion here?
-We were afraid that's why you called...
-Just answer the question.
We stock several different strains
of Yersinia pestis. So, yes.
-Why do you stockpile plague?
-Antibiotics resistance research.
Right, OK. What about Niklas Svensson?
We'll procure a detailed account of
all the projects he's been involved in.
Especially those involving
any other harmful substances.
Yes, of course.
-How's it going?
-Good, I think.
-Do you have a driver's license?
-Yes. Why?
Someone tagged my car. Could you
take it to the shop in Brønshøj?
-Sure.
-Thank you.
Hey. You came after all.
The cops came.
Where was I supposed to go?
-You weren't followed here? Positive?
-Yes, I'm positive.
-Are you OK?
-Yeah.
-It's me.
-I took off. Where are you?
-Don't go home.
-Where should I go?
-Just stay away. I'll sort this.
-Where are you? I can come to you.
-Turn it off.
-Hello?
-I can't talk. I'll call later.
-Turn it off.
Hello?
-It's prepaid. No one has the number.
-They are too close. Turn it off!
Done.
-What do you want?
-Where's the box I left in the hallway?
-I threw it out.
-What? Why?
It was in the hallway. I told you,
trash goes in the hallway for disposal.
-I take it out when I leave.
-This wasn't for disposal.
-Don't leave it in the hallway, then.
-It was pictures and stuff!
-Didn't you notice?
-I didn't look. It was in the hallway.
-Where is it now?
-The waste room. They collect Thursdays.
-It should be there.
-Thank you very much. Bye.
-Was it Jakob? You threw his stuff out?
-Yes. They were in the hallway.
Shouldn't you establish
some common rules?
I did as you said and showed interest
in his work. It annoyed him.
-Maybe show it in another way.
-Maybe you give bad advice.
Three wives, constant infidelity...
You're bad at relationships.
-No, I'm not.
-You can't make one relationship work.
I can, for stretches.
And I'm still married to Mette.
-You're separated.
-Still married.
Why are you married
if you're not living together?
I won't give you any more advice
unless you ask for it.
Good.
-The car will be ready Thursday.
-Thanks.
-I'm off, unless there's anything else.
-No, that'll be all. Thanks.
OK. See you tomorrow.
-I called the cops.
-What?
I was the one who called the cops.
Why the fuck did you that?
You're trying to get us all arrested?
No, them. Only those two.
They've confirmed we're getting
to meet higher-ups tonight.
I need to sort Linus out.
He's all alone...
-He's 13. He can sleep at a friend's.
-Maybe for a night.
Listen, you're going. They said
for all four of us to be there.
-Mads and Niklas.
-They know we're looking for them.
We've talked to everyone around them.
We're staking out known activist
hangouts. Nothing yet.
-What do we know about the women?
-Even less.
None of the people we talked to
mentioned any sisters or partners.
-Sorry.
-Where have you been all day?
I had to go to the ER.
I'm such an idiot.
I had a sandwich that contained nuts.
I've got a bad nut allergy.
-What kind of nut allergy?
-Doesn't matter.
-It could be useful to know.
-Hazelnuts, mostly.
-You're fine now?
-Yes.
-Did you get anywhere with the pics?
-No.
-And Linus?
-He's also stayed underground.
We're staking out the four friends
from the yearbook.
And the apartment,
in case he comes back.
And we're tracking his phone.
All right, thank you.
-Can I get a ride with you?
-Of course.
-Bye, then.
-Bye.
2239 here, we have a visual
of Linus Svensson. Standing by.
-What are you doing here?
-Can I stay here tonight?
-Is this some kind of test?
-No.
Why can't you sleep at home?
Something happened.
All right, come in. Close the door.
Let's hear three short hurrahs
and a long one for Caroline.
And the long one...
-Cheers!
-Thank you. Cheers!
Caroline, you want to see
what I got you?
I thought I'd get my presents
after dinner.
Forty-five is the new thirty.
Now is when life really begins.
It's a cruise for two.
I'm one of the two.
Of course. That's great! Thank you.
Oops. Looks like I've got one more gift.
-What's this?
-Sort of an...emergency number.
For when you're in need
of really great sex.
Caroline, he makes house calls, too.
Happy birthday.
What did Alexander get you?
-These.
-How imaginative.
Cut it out, I wanted these.
I'm happy with them.
Sure, but maybe
you've got other holes to fill.
-You are so obsessed with sex!
-Yes.
Maybe we share other things
that are more important.
Good to be home.
-Thanks for the ride.
-No problem.
You want to get a beer?
Yes. But some other night.
-It's nice to have you on the team.
-Thanks. I think so, too.
-Was this your idea?
-No, it was mine.
-Don't you have other things to do?
-You've lost weight.
Yes. But don't let that fool you.
I'm doing well.
-How are you doing?
-Great.
So one day you just felt so great
you decided to see your son's murderer?
You're not doing great, Martin.
I can tell.
You're angry.
I feel your anger.
I recognize it.
You want it to go away. It won't.
It'll only grow.
Until it becomes who you are.
No. Because I'm not you.
We're not so different.
-So what are you doing here?
-I felt like seeing you. And now I have.
-How is Saga?
-I wouldn't know.
-You haven't seen each other?
-No.
I figured you would stay in touch.
She almost saved your son.
-Hi?
-I need to see the kids.
-They're asleep.
-I need to see them.
Come in.
-Did she get her hair cut?
-Yes. Last week.
I'm missing out on so much.
This is all wrong. I belong here.
You'd never know it.
-No, but I'm trying.
-Are you really?
You come here, get some love from
the kids, then you disappear again.
Do you realize
I don't have a life anymore?
It's just been put on hold. This is
my life now - a house and five kids.
I can't move on. Do I look
for someone new, do I live alone?
-Wait for you to come back?
-I will.
I don't know anything!
I'm living day to day.
Nikolaj woke up.
He's got a temperature.
I got you another gift.
-What's this?
-It's...new boobs.
-New boobs?
-Well, no, not new ones...
It's for...breast implants.
You want me to get bigger boobs?
Not me, but you're always saying
they're a little saggy and sad.
Yes, but...that's just how I look.
-I thought you'd be happy.
-That's what you thought?
Did you manage to find
a new keynote speaker?
Yes, most likely.
Tomorrow I'll know for sure.
Well, fingers crossed.
Hey. You OK? Where are you?
At a friend's. When can I see you?
-Tomorrow, I hope.
-Niklas!
I've got to go. I love you, Linus.
It's all going to be fine.
-Go to bed.
-But where...?
-Jakob?
-Yeah?
What's this?
What have you done with my files?
I put them on the desk for now.
I'll sort it out tomorrow.
-You don't have any pictures out.
-No.
-Why not?
-It's unnecessary.
You never mention your family.
My sister's dead.
I never see my parents.
-Why not?
-They're no good for me.
-And your sister?
-She jumped in front of a train at 14.
Why haven't you told me?
Is it important?
Does it affect your opinion of me?
No, but I want to know all about you.
But that's impossible.
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
-Hi.
-Linus made a call.
-To whom?
-To a prepaid. We assume it's Niklas.
It's still on,
so I'll locate it any minute.
Let's see...
-It's the old industrial area.
-I'll go there right away.
Hey, Saga. This is not a good time.
-We've located Niklas.
-I'll be there right away.
Good!
Subtitles: Mario Bernengo
TC:subtitling
Edited by thedude95