-Who owns the boat?
-Marcus Stenberg.
Why would anyone steal your ship,
chain five people and run it aground?
A woman's died from a poisoned apple.
Negative human impact
on the environment - hence the symbol.
A pathos-driven eco-terrorism of sorts?
-We had a death.
-How do you know Viktoria Nordgren?
She's the summit's keynote speaker.
I'd like for you to do
my sister Viktoria's memoirs.
-How is she?
-The doctors give her six months.
Knowing her, that means 18 months.
-I want to write a book.
-Everyone does.
I've known a lot of interesting women.
Famous women.
This is a copy of the case file
Saga and I are working on.
-He's in jail for life!
-I'll make sure he knows what he did.
One day you just felt so great
you decided to see your son's murderer?
Someone logged in
with the handle "Mother Of Three."
-It's the four from the videos.
-Probably.
They were locked in,
and gas was pumped in.
-Traced "Mother Of Three"?
-Not yet.
They discussed a "birthday party"
and "graduation." There are more.
-This came a few minutes ago.
-She's involved with animal testing.
-Is this a new group?
-These groups tend to work in cells.
EPISODE 6
Get down! Take off your mask!
You're not doing yourself any favors
by not cooperating.
-I'll be back later.
-Sure thing.
His lawyer advised him
not to talk to us.
Try your luck with Thomas Dahlberg.
He seemed more cooperative.
At least in the initial interviews.
-Are you OK?
-Yes.
-I mean, you were attacked.
-It was poorly planned and executed.
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
These are the people
that died from pneumonic plague...
These were poisoned...
These died in the harbor explosion.
All in all, twelve people.
Hang on...
I've got nothing to do with this.
Four people donning identical masks
to yours have claimed responsibility.
But this was some other people,
this wasn't us...
These are the people that died. Right?
The prosecutor sees these
as acts of terror.
Knowledge of the attacks and group
affiliation is enough for a conviction.
But we're not affiliated.
Not with any group.
-Why did you attack me?
-Well...
We thought maybe we'd be able to
render you in exchange for safe conduct.
-That we'd get away.
-That would never have worked.
-Tell me about the golden toads.
-About the what, now...?
-Why did you stop using them?
-We've never used them.
We saw the animal-mask videos
and thought it'd be a good idea...
-For our cause.
-Your cause?
Yes, animal rights. We kind of went
with what they were doing.
-But... Yeah.
-Who's giving you your assignments?
-What do you mean?
-Your orders? Who decides what to do?
Well, that's...
That's Carl.
Well, that's... That's Carl.
-Carl Sjöberg?
-Yes, that's correct.
So Carl Sjöberg planned what you did?
Yes.
They're not pertinent to our case.
They're copycats.
No connection to Mother Of Three.
They're guilty of abduction and assault.
I'd like to apologize
for what happened here yesterday.
-Did you talk to Martin?
-About what?
He said you were out of line and should
apologize. Maybe he'd talked to you.
No, I... Unlike some, I don't need
Martin to tell me when I'm out of line.
By "some" you mean me?
I apologize
for what happened here yesterday.
Thank you.
-Alexander!
-Yes?
-Have you seen my cell phone?
-Um... No.
-Can I borrow yours?
-Why? I need it.
To call my cell!
Thank you...
-What's it doing here?
-How should I know? It's your phone!
-See you tonight.
-Yeah, see you.
Right. I gotta go now.
-Can I have a word?
-Sure.
Nikolaj, I'm stepping out.
You can still see us.
-Martin.
-Thorsen.
-Mette.
I've been told Nikolaj had a cold
and a sore throat a few weeks ago.
So this is probably acute
post-streptococcal glomerulonephritis.
It means the throat infection
has spread to the kidneys.
It's harmless. Most patients make
a full recovery within a couple of weeks
and the kidneys resume normal function.
But I'd still like to do a biopsy on Nikolaj
to eliminate any other possibilities.
-Of course.
-What are the other possibilities?
The same symptoms occur
in other types of glomerulonephritis.
-In that case, it's a bit more serious.
-How much more serious?
In that case, we start a treatment with
steroids and chemotherapy immediately.
So I'd really like to do a biopsy
on Nikolaj's kidney as soon as possible.
Great.
The new group were just copycats.
So the four that died
in the container were the only cell.
Any remaining cells would have reacted
to the copycats stealing the spotlight.
So only Mother Of Three is left.
How long are you staying here?
As long as it takes.
-Has he been diagnosed?
-Something with the kidneys.
They're not working properly.
It was called...
-Glomerulonephritis or something.
-Glomerulonephritis?
Call me when you're ready
to come back to work.
Thank you.
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
Meet me outside Glostrup Hospital.
Yes, as soon as possible. All right.
-I've been to Mette's house.
-Yes, and?
-We're going to arrest Anna-Dea.
-Why?
-What are you doing here?
-I need to talk to Anna-Dea.
Could you step outside with me?
-Who are you?
-I'm Martin's boss.
-Are you coming? It's important.
-No. I can't. I'm sitting here...
I can't right now.
Anna-Dea, please step outside with us.
She's poisoned Nikolaj.
"Munchausen by proxy."
She makes him ill by administering
blood pressure medication to him.
-It's not true...
-Why did you do that?
-It's a mental illness.
-No!
It makes you crave validation
and attention.
She hates me, Martin.
Don't believe her. It's a lie.
-She puts it in his juice.
-No...
I didn't do anything.
-Get her out of here.
-No, Martin!
Saga is the crazy one!
And Nikolaj needs me!
Munchausen?
I've never seen that before.
It's usually the parents.
-What'll happen to him now?
-He'll get better.
She stopped poisoning him
once he was admitted.
The idea is for him to be discharged
and then fall ill again.
-How come you know so much about it?
-I just do.
-Yes...
-All right.
-Saga, wait for me downstairs.
-You're coming back to work?
-I'm coming.
-Good.
I don't think I could bury another one.
But he was never supposed to die.
-He was supposed to be sick forever.
-More or less, yes.
-Thank you for saving him from that.
-You're welcome.
I mean it, Saga. Thank you.
Thank you.
All done? Can we go?
-I'll need another minute.
-Then I'll go wait in the car.
Caroline, did you see what happened?
-No, what is it?
-Claudio was murdered.
What? When did that happen?
It says that he died last night.
In a park. Some crazy person killed him.
You'll get drawn into this now.
Me? How?
It must've happened after he saw you.
What do you mean? I didn't see him.
But... Did you cancel?
No, I hadn't... What do you mean?
He texted me that you were meeting.
Did he say how we agreed to meet?
You texted him, I think. Do you contact
each other in any other way?
No. Listen, I have a meeting.
I have to go. I'll talk to you later.
Dharma, can you help me with something?
I accidentally deleted some messages.
Can you retrieve them in any way?
-Yeah, I think so.
-Thanks.
How did you figure it out?
The signs were there
if you knew what to look for.
-And you knew?
-Yes.
How did you know?
I've seen it before, on a case.
Jakob's mother is coming
to dinner tonight.
-First time?
-Yes.
Nervous?
Mothers tend to dislike their sons'
partners more than their daughters'.
I never got along with any of my
mother-in-laws, if it's any consolation.
-Why would it be?
-Anyway, that's how it was.
You don't think it's because
you always cheated on their daughters?
We've got a body.
Claus Damgaard, goes by the name
of Claudio, 44 years of age.
A Copenhagen resident,
found dead in a park there last night.
-A Dane dead in Denmark? Why is he here?
-He's for you.
-But why?
-He's been battered, as you can see.
But that wasn't the cause of death.
The Danes found the same poison
as in the fruits and shellfish
and which killed that woman
in the hospital.
-What was his line of business?
-He sold exclusive sexual services.
Apparently, he was expensive.
Send me a report.
-He had a small penis.
-I didn't notice.
He did. It'd be bigger erect,
but it was definitely not big.
-Why are we talking about this?
-It's weird.
-What's that got to do with anything?
-Dunno.
I just expected other physical
attributes if he's so successful.
So you think size matters?
He fulfilled fantasies. Few women
fantasize about small penises.
He could still be good at sex.
I'm not saying he wasn't.
Jakob is very good at sex.
-His is barely 4 inches.
-Stop!
I don't need to hear about the size
of your boyfriend's dick.
-Why not?
-Drop it.
I know what you want to ask me,
and I'm not gonna tell you.
-What?
-Forget it.
-What are you doing?
-What does it look like?
-But...why?
-It was on my list.
-What list?
-I'm dying, I'm getting a tattoo...
I've got a list. How hard is it
to figure out? It's a bucket list.
-Have you thought about the memoirs?
-Yeah, not on my list.
I met a friend last night
who's a publisher.
-She sounded enthused.
-I don't have time, Oliver.
She'll do the writing, I'll assist
with the research. Just meet her.
Why are you so eager about the book?
What you've accomplished is astonishing.
Why not tell people about it? I want
everyone to be as proud of you as I am.
-You're sucking up.
-Yes, I'm sorry.
I'll meet her. We'll see.
Briefing.
Claus Damgaard, a.k.a. Claudio.
44 years of age.
Copenhagen resident, prostitute, likely
active on both sides of the strait.
Beat up and killed with the same poison.
-Hence the connection.
-It can't get leaked to the press.
If Claudio was hooking
maybe the connection is just sex.
It could mean Mother Of Three
actually is a woman.
-We need to know who his clients were.
-How? They won't turn themselves in.
-His cell phone.
-None was found on his person.
-No phone plan, say Danish police.
-Are we searching his apartment?
Pernille, ask the Danish police
to send us the file.
What fun do you have for me today?
Go through the case again
for anything we've overlooked.
-You realize the sheer volume of that?
-Yes.
-I've printed them out for you.
-Thanks.
THE PAVILION AT THE PARK AT 9 P.M.
GREAT SEE YOU THERE.
-Is anything wrong?
-No. It's just...
Someone sent messages from my phone.
I'll figure it out. Thank you.
-Could you close the door, please?
-Yeah.
Hello, my name is Caroline Brandstrup.
I'd like to report a crime.
Alexander Brandstrup? Police.
Will you come with us?
Send him over straight away.
All right, thanks. That was Lillian.
They got someone for Damgaard's murder.
They'll bring him over.
-Who's that?
-Claus Damgaard.
He was found dead last night.
Don't know him. Never seen him before.
I've got nothing to do with this.
Where were you last night
between 9 and 12 p.m.?
-At the office.
-Alone?
Your wife claims
you're involved in this.
She's mistaken.
-Sure you don't want a lawyer present?
-I'm a lawyer myself.
-Not a criminal lawyer.
-I'm sure I'll manage.
People in your position
usually think so.
-You've never met Damgaard?
-No.
Never contacted him
using your wife's cell phone?
No.
So when we search your home,
office, car, we'll find nothing?
No.
What... What's this?
Pictures of the people that died
from the same poison as Damgaard.
-He was poisoned?
-How do you think he died?
I... I don't know.
He slept with your wife?
Was that why you beat him first?
Your field is
international environmental law.
How's that going, you think?
-Are we making small talk while we wait?
-No.
OK.
They found traces of blood in your car
and on the snow shovel.
You don't think the wounds
on Claus Damgaard will match?
-I didn't kill him.
-No. Not with the snow shovel.
He took his wife's cell phone.
He set up a meeting and beat him up.
He said Damgaard was alive
when he left him.
Techs found no poison in his home,
but they found a gun.
We'll see if the ballistics
match with Laura.
If Alexander left him beaten but alive,
the perp must've showed up right after.
-Right.
-How did he know where they were?
Alexander's wife had
a cell number for Claudio.
I'll get John to check the traffic
with the carrier.
-So you think Alexander shot Laura?
-Could be.
At least we'll have time
to check his alibi.
-Good luck tonight.
-With what?
Isn't your mother-in-law coming?
Just act like you're interested
and you'll be fine.
-But I'm not interested.
-No, but still.
Ask her where she lives,
what she does... Normal stuff.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
-Yes. Thanks.
-Thanks for saving Nikolaj.
You've said that many times now.
-Pernille. Want a ride?
-Sure, I'd love to.
-Five minutes.
-OK.
-I'm glad your son's doing better.
-Thank you.
-I need you to do me a favor.
-OK.
You have access
to the Swedish archives, right?
-Can you find an old case file?
-I need to know a little bit more.
16 years ago. 14-year-old girl jumps
in front of a train here in Malmö.
-Do you have a name?
-Yes.
Norén.
Can we keep it between us?
OK.
-But it'll cost you.
-OK...?
-The cups.
-Get out of here!
-Is that it?
-I can think of more fun stuff.
I sure hope so.
Where is the real proposal?
That is the real proposal.
I know it's not what you want, Richard,
but it's the best offer you'll get.
-I don't think so.
-I do.
FDA won't approve Camprax in the US,
your Restopolin and Trombolec patents
expire in less than six months,
so how will you make money?
-FDA hasn't decided on Camprax yet.
-Not officially.
If it is as you say,
then why do you want to buy us?
Because you don't want to sell.
At least not to me.
-I can sell to someone else.
-Sure...
And who is going to buy
once word gets out on Camprax?
A dying woman's
last desperate attempt to get her will.
Yeah... Seems your company and I
have about the same amount of time left.
Do you know what you can do with this?
Shove it up your pussy!
Up my pussy, you say? I'll be damned.
Once you're buried
and you feel your coffin shaking,
that's us, dancing on your grave.
I take it that's a no, then?
Take it as a declaration of war.
-So I gave up my place and moved in.
-You did the right thing.
-Look who it is!
-There she is! Hi.
This is Saga.
Jeanette, my mother.
-I know.
-Pleased to meet you.
Saga works on the plague
and poisonings...
-Right, the gold frog.
-It's a toad, Mom. Not a frog.
I'm sorry. And how is that going?
I can't discuss the case with civilians.
-I understand.
-I'm just going to see to dinner.
Jakob's brother is a cop, too.
Maybe you already knew.
-Yes.
-In Gävle.
Yes, I know.
-Nice place you guys have here.
-It's my place.
I know, but you live here together.
That's what I meant.
-Where do you live?
-I still live in Växjö.
That's where Jakob was born.
I'm sure you knew that.
-No. You like it?
-Yes, it's nice.
But it's a bit on the quiet side.
-It's good you don't live nearby.
-What do you mean by that?
Statistically, that could aggravate
relationship problems.
The parents are perceived
to interfere too much.
-You've experienced this?
-No. I've read about it.
I've never had a mother-in-law.
And still, you want me
as far away as possible?
Dinner's ready, you guys!
Come and sit down.
Yummy.
I stopped by the Indian restaurant.
-I'm not hungry.
-No, but you might get hungry.
-Are we waiting for your friend?
-He's not coming.
-Why not?
-I forgot to call him.
Did you read it?
Maybe.
This is your last chance.
I'm taking it with me today.
-Why?
-Lillian wants it back.
She chewed me out
when she learned I gave it to you.
Should I feel sorry for you
or be grateful for reading it?
So you did read it?
-Yes.
-Good.
I want to hear your thoughts.
-So I talk, you write?
-Yes. That's the gist of it.
-And what do I talk about?
-Everything.
As far as I'm concerned,
the more, the better.
Then we'll edit the text
together afterwards.
-What if I'm not alive then?
-Then I'll take it up with your brother.
If we're to do this, he stays out of it.
He knows nothing, he reads nothing.
-Can I ask why?
-No. Not at this stage.
OK.
If I'm going to tell all,
the same goes for you.
Tell me something about you
no one else knows.
Is this some kind of test?
More like a...job interview,
I guess you could call it.
I've had sex with that guy.
So have I, actually.
And no one knows about it?
-Yes. My sister.
-Then it doesn't count.
Tell me something else - a secret.
I'm fucking my sister's husband.
Call my assistant and set up a meeting.
I'll see myself out.
Pernille thinks Mother Of Three
could be a woman.
Nothing in here points
to anything specific.
I wouldn't rule anything out.
-Nikolaj is in the hospital.
-Why are we talking about him?
-Just making small talk.
-You came here to make small talk?
No. I came here to work,
and we've done that now.
-This wasn't work.
-Whatever. You weren't hungry, either.
-I have to go back.
-Someone waiting for you?
-Hey, kids.
-Hi, Dad.
-Hello...
-Hello.
-Did you eat?
-Yes.
-They asked about Anna-Dea.
-Oh? What did you tell them?
That she got caught stealing
from people, so the police took her.
-I told them she was a thief.
-OK.
What should I have said?
That she tried to kill their brother?
No, no.
They miss her, but I couldn't pretend
that she was a good person.
Of course not.
I think you said the right thing.
-I'm relieving my mom at the hospital.
-I'll be here.
-I think I'll stay the night.
-I can stay for as long as you need.
-Get going.
-Yes. See you.
-Hey, kids! Make room for Dad!
-Yeah!
-I want to have sex.
-Now?
-Yes.
-But my mom is right in there.
Yes, but we can have sex here.
-She'll hear us.
-Does that bother you?
Well, yeah, a little.
Why? You're an adult.
She must know you're sexually active.
Knowing is one thing. Hearing me
have it is completely different.
-You're sure?
-It's tempting, but yes.
OK.
Hey. Sorry, I thought you were going
to stay the night at the hospital.
My mom stayed.
Will you put your arms around me?
Morning!
-Hello.
-You know how many we're dealing with?
-No. A lot, apparently.
-Did the divers touch anything?
-No. They pried open the cabin.
They turned around immediately when
they saw what was in it. So they said.
-It was sunk, right?
-It would appear so.
We're tracking down the owner.
Will you hold it for me?
What are you doing?
I'm masturbating.
I can see that, but I'm right here!
You didn't want to have sex
because of your mom.
No, but I'm still lying right here!
I've read a lot of men are turned on
by watching their girlfriend masturbate.
I'm going to fix some breakfast.
I'm almost done.
-Morning.
-Morning, Mom.
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
-It's Pernille. This a bad time?
-Yes. What do you want?
Some divers found a boat
with the bones of seven corpses.
They were all shot, it seems.
The police tracked down the owner
and contacted us.
-Why is that?
-Guess who the owner is?
-No. I never make guesses.
-Marcus Stenberg.
OK. Thanks.
There were seven dead people
on your boat.
What are you talking about?
Where was this?
We found seven dead people
on your sunken boat.
That's what we'd like
to talk to you about.
-I don't know...
-What don't you know?
It was stolen...many years ago.
I was on vacation with my then-wife.
I got home, it was missing.
I reported it, claimed the insurance...
I don't understand...what's happening.
I know nothing about any of this.
Who beat you?
I've got some...problems,
but nothing related to any murders.
What problems?
About a year ago, the business wasn't
going too well, I needed new capital.
So this other firm, Söderberg & Joost,
came in with their capital
in exchange for a minority stake
in the company.
And I suspect, or I know, that they
are using the firm for money laundering
and I also think they put
their goods in my shipments.
-They're smuggling?
-I don't know, I think so.
Can you help me?
-Let's say we believe you...
-It's the truth.
Two of your boats have turned up
in our investigation!
If you don't know anything about this...
...at least you ought to be interested
in knowing who's after you.
Stenberg reported his motor boat
stolen some nine years ago.
He got his insurance money.
That was that.
I want all missing persons from March
nine years ago and the past six months.
-Age groups?
-All. Men, women.
Primarily in Denmark and Sweden.
We found nothing at his home
but this old report says
that Stenberg was
in Thailand at the time.
Maybe he ordered the sinking
and left to have an alibi.
That's not enough to hold him.
Pernille, go show Laura pictures
of Alexander and Stenberg.
Alexander Brandstrup has an alibi
for the murder of Beate.
He was in Stockholm. And the bullets
from his gun don't match.
If Alexander didn't do it, how did
the murderer know where Claudio was?
Claudio's last four texts were sent
to and from a prepaid phone.
-And you can't trace that?
-We tried.
-It must be off or destroyed.
-What did the texts say?
"Claudissimio, where are you?
I'm longing for you."
"On my way to the park.
Were we meeting today?"
"No, just missing you.
Where in the park can we meet?"
"By the pavilion. Not a good idea.
I'll get back to you."
-That supports Alexander's version.
-And that it's a woman.
"Claudissimio" definitely banged her.
-Anyone got anything else?
-I do. This Boris Williams...
Poisoned-meat guy. He reported
a burglary two days before he died.
-What's that got to do with anything?
-I don't know.
Saga asked me
to go through the case from scratch.
-Yes. Keep going.
-Yes...
-I stayed the night at Mette's place.
-Oh?
It was so nice to sleep at home again.
You've never lived there.
It can't be home to you.
Home to me is to be
with the whole family.
-Is Nikolaj back?
-OK, almost the whole family.
You know very few separated couples
manage to make it work again?
Why would you say that?
Can I not be a little bit happy?
Yes, but realistic expectations for the
future may help avoid disappointment.
-Could you please not talk?
-Yes.
Thank you.
So... Are you doing the list?
Yes... Fugu.
Extremely poisonous Japanese blowfish.
-I know what Fugu is.
-Want some?
No, thanks. I just wanted to ask
if you'd met with Bodil.
Yes. You'll have your book.
-So you liked her?
-I'm sure we'll get along.
-Great. I'll draw up contracts and...
-Do that.
-You know Richard Strandh, right?
-Yes. I met with him yesterday. Why?
He was beat up last night
in a parking garage.
-Three guys just jumped him, apparently.
-Oh...
All right, talk to you later.
We can't board yet. They're not sure
they've located all the body parts.
How did it go with your mother-in-law?
Good. I asked where she lived.
-Saga!
-Yes?
-What's that?
-A breast implant.
-A breast implant?
-Yes.
-Where did you find it?
-Down there.
Try to find a serial number
and send it over. Thanks.
-A breast implant?
-You put it in your boobs to get...
Saga, I know what it is.
-OK. So you're going now?
-Yes...
-Well, don't go too far.
-No. Ystad. Is that OK?
That's OK.
-Did Laura recognize anyone?
-No.
We have information
from Copenhagen.
A witness saw a white car parked
near where Damgaard was murdered.
-Did she see the plates?
-She took a photo.
-It was reported stolen.
-It's like the one from Laura's video.
Who's the owner?
-Theodor Bruse in Malmö.
-Send the address.
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
Is this your car?
-Could be.
-You're the registered owner.
-So you knew it was mine?
-Yes.
Your car was seen at a crime scene.
What do you have to say to that?
It's mine, but I never drive it.
-Who does, then?
-I don't know.
-Why don't you know?
-I don't know who drives any of my cars.
-You're saying you have more cars?
-Yeah. I have more.
-He owns 187 cars.
-187 cars? Then it's in name only.
-What do you mean?
-He's someone without assets.
He has vehicles in his name
to get the drivers out of tickets.
And they never know who the drivers are.
We'll hold Bruse and see if he knows who
asked him to be the owner of that car.
The police have released a photo
of the boat that divers found yesterday.
They found the remains
of seven individuals on board the boat.
The boat was stolen
from Wimar's Marina...
-Information. How may I help you?
-I need a number.
-Hello?
-I'm the one who sank your boat.
You forgot to tell me
there were seven people in it.
It's going to cost you.
Subtitles: Mario Bernengo
TC:subtitling
Edited by thedude95