-Who owns the boat?
-Marcus Stenberg.
Why would anyone steal your ship,
chain five people and run it aground?
Negative human impact
on the environment - hence the symbol.
A pathos-driven eco-terrorism of sorts?
It could be a Niklas Svensson
at Medisonus in Copenhagen.
We specialize in third-world
vaccines and maladies.
-Niklas Svensson?
-You'll get a report on his projects.
Someone logged in
with the handle "Mother Of Three".
-I can't recall.
-You traced Mother Of Three?
Not yet, but they've discussed
a "birthday party" and a "graduation."
I get a text with a pick-up location.
I let it disappear with the other waste.
I'd like for you to do
my sister Viktoria's memoirs.
-How is she?
-The doctors give her six months.
-Tell me something no one knows.
-I'm fucking my sister's husband.
-What's my phone doing here?
-How should I know?
He took his wife's cell phone.
He set up a meeting and beat him up.
Some divers found a boat
with seven corpses.
-Marcus Stenberg.
-I'm the one who sank your boat.
You forgot to tell me
there were seven people in it.
It's going to cost you.
EPISODE 7
Hey.
-Any luck?
-Nothing. What about over here?
-Same here.
-We'll have to try some other time.
-Or we could go fishing.
-That doesn't count.
-It's killing your own food.
-I just changed my list.
I need to shoot my own food.
-What are you doing?
-I'll be right back.
-Viktoria?
-Wait, I'll be right back.
I'm the one who sank your boat.
You forgot to tell me
there were seven people in it.
It's going to cost you.
-Who is this?
-I sank your boat.
I want 100,000 kroner
or I'll tell the police.
We tap your phone,
and he calls you. Who is he?
-I've got nothing to do with this.
-It's the third time you're here.
-But I've got nothing to do with this!
-The caller implied the opposite.
Yes, but I don't know this person.
I didn't...
I didn't ask anyone to sink my boat.
It was stolen when I was on vacation.
So someone steals your boat and sinks it
with seven people on board...
-Nine years later they blackmail you.
-Yes, it...
-And you're clueless?
-It sounds totally nuts, but...yes.
-But I don't believe you. Do you?
-The coincidence is highly unlikely.
Especially since the ship
that ran aground was yours, too.
So she doesn't believe you, either.
I hope you don't have any plans today.
This will take a while.
-Hi, honey.
-Hi.
-Did you get anything?
-Yes, kind of.
-What's that?
-It's a hen.
-What will you do with it?
-Not me. You.
I'm thinking something with curry
for dinner tonight.
I'm taking a shower.
Then I'm going to work.
-Thanks for taking me out.
-No problem. I had a good time.
Where did you get the hen?
We drove onto a farm.
I went in and shot it.
It was easy, it was caged.
Tattoos, Fugu, now you've shot a hen.
-Is this as insane as it gets?
-I don't know.
Hey...
-I know how you feel.
-No, you have no fucking idea.
I'm doing all I can to help you.
That's not very much,
you know it and I know it.
Hey, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm tired, and I'm a little achy.
Well... You bring the wine.
Will do. See you.
-Did she leave?
-Yes.
-Why don't you join me?
-I have to tend to this thing.
No. It's not flying anywhere.
Come on.
-Julian Madsen?
-No.
-Look at the picture.
Where do you get your IT set-up from?
I'm not the IT manager,
but I can find out.
-You know Claus Damgaard?
-No.
-He goes by Claudio.
-I don't know a Claus or a Claudio.
Where were you last Thursday
between 12 and 3 p.m.?
-I don't know.
-You tried to kill Laura Möllberg again.
-I don't know a Laura Möllberg!
-Look at the picture.
I'm looking at it,
and I don't know a Laura Möllberg.
Here's a list with times and dates.
Write where you were.
-I need my calendar for that.
-Where is it?
In my phone.
I need Marcus Stenberg's phone.
Are you done with it?
Yeah, nothing tying him
to anything or anyone.
Thanks.
I've got nothing on the 18th.
Of course not.
PRIVATE NUMBER
Pick up on speaker.
Don't mention us or where you are.
-Marcus Stenberg.
-Got the money?
-No, not yet.
-I want them in an hour.
-I need more time for that kind of sum.
-How much more time?
Three hours.
-Where are you now?
-Malmö.
OK, listen. Meet me on the footbridge
by Svågertorp station in three hours.
I'll be there.
-So how do we do this?
-Hang on, I need to... There we go.
Right. Well, how do you want to do it?
Asking me questions seems easiest.
This can't take all day.
OK... What are your thoughts
when you hear the word "passion"?
What the hell kind of question is that?
Your passion, what's important to you,
it says who you are.
I don't want this book to be some mushy
inspiration piece for other women.
-How do you want it to be, then?
-Honest.
It will be if you answer in honesty.
Well, ask questions that make sense.
OK. OK...
I'll start a sentence and then you say
the first thing that comes to mind.
-Sure.
-I am...
-Lonely.
-OK...
That's not how you come across.
-Was that the wrong answer?
-No, no. There are no wrong answers.
I just thought...
Your brother lives across the street...
But we're not talking
about him now, are we?
No. All right, let's keep going.
I am not...
Content.
-Not with anything?
-No.
I'm very hard to please, I think.
I would never allow...
...anything to stand in my way.
We need to decide
if we want bottled or tap water.
-Your call.
-Tap water saves us 50 percent.
We'll take that, then. After all,
it's an environmental conference.
How are you?
-I'm getting a divorce.
-I'm sorry.
-You know what he did, right?
-Yes, it's in the papers.
It says "crime of passion"
but I didn't have sex with him.
-I didn't read anything about that.
-It seems like you're the only one.
Let me know
if there's anything I can do.
Yes, actually there is.
Can you have a look at this one, too?
Of course.
OK, listen up. Stenberg is approaching.
Isak, in position in the tunnel.
OK, we'll hang back. Let us know
when Stenberg is in position.
Marcus, stop looking at us.
-Is that him?
-How should I know?
I don't know what he looks like.
He's waiting for someone.
Marcus... Establish contact.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
Is it me...you're looking for?
Who the hell are you?
Go!
Don't move!
Ramon Bodski: multiple charges,
you did three years for robbery.
-I've stayed away from that shit since.
-Except for blackmail.
Nine years ago you sank this boat.
I didn't know there were people in it.
What happened?
-I was contacted.
-By whom, and when?
He called... A man called me.
He offered me 25,000 kroner
to sink his boat.
-Was it Marcus Stenberg, the owner?
-Yes, that's what he said.
It was an insurance thing.
I didn't know about the people.
"Who the hell are you?" you said
when you saw him at the station.
That was Marcus Stenberg,
the boat's owner.
-No, he didn't ask me to sink it.
-Sure? It's been nine years.
-It wasn't him.
-So what did he look like?
Not like that, that's for sure.
-Describe him to a composite artist.
-It's been nine years.
-But you weren't thrown on the phone.
-By what?
By the language. So the man
who hired you spoke Swedish?
Yes.
The statute on the insurance fraud is up.
-Ramon was our only tie to the murders.
-Do we really think he was clueless?
If I wanted my boat sunk I'd never say
my name. I say Stenberg's being framed.
So we need to focus on him.
Get a background check on him.
Ex-wives, colleagues...
-We did that.
-Do it over.
-What about Ramon?
-We hold him on the blackmail charge?
Hans is talking to the prosecutor.
-Yes? What do you want?
-It's Hans.
-Yes, I know. What do you want?
-I want you all to get here.
Romstock chemical company.
They make propylene oxide.
The cooling system collapsed
about 30 minutes ago.
This plant is controversial.
There's a drinking water basin nearby.
The leak is major.
They've evacuated surrounding buildings.
Don't they have a security system?
Two automatic, one manual.
None of them worked.
This was delivered express, minutes
before the cooling system collapsed.
Hey...
How are you? Hey, honey, it's Daddy.
Were you dreaming?
You were dreaming, weren't you?
What's the matter?
I saw him.
I saw the man who shot me.
In my dream, I saw him!
-We have to call the police.
-Sure, I will. Right away.
-Now!
-Relax, I will.
You just relax.
-What did they say?
-They weren't in.
-They were busy with something urgent.
-With what?
I don't know what.
I never got to talk to them.
They were out. I left a message.
The package had been sitting at the depot
for two weeks before being delivered.
-They know who left it?
-Yep. Niklas Svensson.
The delivery guy was able to finger him.
Svensson had asked that the package be
delivered today between 12.30 and 1 p.m.
You're right, Saga.
He's not starting a new cell.
-It's not needed.
-He's getting more invisible.
-No one's invisible.
-No. I didn't mean it literally.
No, neither did I. You meant,
everyone leaves a trace, right? Me, too.
I talked to Lillian.
We'll keep quiet about the golden toad.
We don't want to people to panic.
They think it's over.
-But it's not over.
-Saga? You have a visitor.
-So this is where you work?
-Yes. What do you want?
I wanted to say goodbye.
I go back today.
It's been very...interesting
spending this time with you guys.
Many people use "interesting" if they
dislike something, but won't admit it.
Is that so?
-What did I do wrong?
-You didn't do anything wrong.
You're just a little too...outspoken
for my taste, to be honest.
And you seem to be totally
and utterly uninterested
in everything outside your own world.
Then why are you here?
I'd like to ask you something personal,
though maybe it's none of my business.
-If you think about the future...
-I don't think about the future.
OK, say you're making plans.
Do you see yourself with Jakob?
Do you see any children?
-You want to be a grandmother!
-I am.
Jakob has a brother with two daughters.
You have a picture of them at home.
Oh.
Saga, Jakob is very much
in love with you.
Yes.
-Are you in love with him?
-I'm his girlfriend.
-Is that going OK, you think?
-I doubt it.
You can go in and save her, if you want.
We have a hit on the breast implant.
It's from a Danish company, Esteem.
Sold to the West clinic in 2000.
-Perfect. Nice work.
-And... then there's the suicide.
Saga's sister was called Jennifer Norén.
-Should you really read it?
-Why not?
If she wanted you to know,
she probably would've told you.
Yeah, probably.
Sorry to disturb. I'm Martin Rohde,
Saga's colleague. Sorry, we need to go.
Here. The breast implants.
-OK. You're coming?
-Yes.
-Pernille can see you out.
-Thanks, I'll manage.
Things went well today again
with the in-law?
-A little worse, I think.
-What did you talk about?
She asked if I wanted kids
and if I was in love with Jakob.
-And what did you answer?
-I didn't, really.
Why not just say
you were in love with Jakob?
If I had been in love, my brain would
have released serotonin or dopamine.
I'd feel euphoria,
happiness or contentment.
-So love to you is a chemical reaction?
-Not just me, all people. It's science.
-So maybe it went a little worse.
-Yes.
That's what I said.
Hello...
You scared me! Hi, Caroline.
How long have you been here?
-A while.
-How have you been today?
Do you know how the police found out
about Alexander and Claudio?
-You reported him.
-Yes. But how did I find out?
-I don't know.
-Alexander took my cell phone.
He set up a meeting pretending to be me.
Then he deleted the text messages.
A colleague restored them.
It was apparently very easy.
OK...
I found a phone today.
In Alexander's clothes.
Apparently he had several cell phones.
I had the text messages
on that one restored, too.
Caroline, listen...
Now I know how he felt
when he thought I was cheating on him.
No! Don't you touch me.
Just listen to me.
I never want to see you again.
-Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
-Martin Rohde.
We found an implant.
We need some information.
-How do you "find" an implant?
-The body around it had dissolved.
-And you're sure it's ours?
-We have a serial number.
We don't store them in a database,
only in the patient's file.
But you keep the files in a database?
Yes, but you can't search
for a serial number.
So you'll have to go through
all the files manually.
She died in March
nine years ago, so before then.
Esteem delivered the implant
in the spring of 2000.
That won't help. We had
our 20th anniversary last spring.
We were four surgeons at the time.
There are 600-700 files. Maybe more.
-Can we take them with us?
-No.
You can't even read them
unless you get a warrant.
-You get a warrant, I'll call Pernille.
-Yeah.
Have you ever felt
a pair of silicone breasts?
-Yes.
-How were they?
They were... OK. Why do you ask?
I was just wondering.
Does Mette have silicone breasts?
No. Why do you want to know this?
-She's got such nice tits.
-Yes. She does.
The prosecutor let Ramon go.
And he didn't want protection.
-But someone's tailing him?
-No, I don't think so.
Hi, it's me. When did you let Ramon go?
Where was he going?
We have the warrant, so just go in.
-How many were there?
-Around 600.
-Got an address?
-I'll call when we have something.
We've got an address.
Still no answer.
What the fuck?
Why didn't we put a tail on him?
Lack of manpower.
Resources were tied up nationally.
And now he could be dead.
-He got a sketch made.
-The artist says we can't use it.
-Why the hell not?
-Ramon wasn't sure about anything.
He kept changing his mind.
Head shape, facial features...
-Hair color, eye color...
-Then what's it doing there?
-Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
-Found her. Karin Miller.
-21 years old, from Malmö.
-Got an address?
-It's over ten years old.
-Is there a next of kin in the file?
-Her parents. Sven and Ellen Miller.
-Sven and Ellen Miller.
-Tell her "nice work."
-Hello, wait!
-Martin says to tell you "nice work."
-Thanks.
-Tell him I said hi.
-You're welcome. Bye.
I had an inkling that Karin was dead.
She wouldn't just disappear like that.
-Was she still living at home?
-Yes.
Until the summer,
then she was going to Spain.
She was going to train
to be a bartender or something.
-Did she have a job?
-Yes, in eldercare. Part-time.
She had breast implants.
How could she afford them?
I don't know.
She must have saved up for it.
-Can we see her room?
-No. There's nothing left.
Ellen and I cleaned it out
five or six years ago.
Then, well, Ellen got cancer...
Did she ever mention
the name Marcus Stenberg?
Stenberg?
No, I've never heard that name.
She was found with six others.
Did any of her friends disappear?
-So you don't know who they are?
-No, not yet.
No, I don't know.
Thank you for your help.
Let me go! Let me go!
Hey...
-Where have you been?
-Romstock chemical plant.
Did you know Julian Madsen's firm
did part of their software?
-That's why the cooling system was off?
-Exactly.
Certain files had a virus that wrote
new code for the cooling system by the...
-The propylene oxide production.
-Right. It knocked it out.
Remember the chat convo with
Mother Of Three from Julian's computer?
-The birthday party and the graduation?
-Yes.
Romstock started its production
exactly three years ago today.
So the question is,
what's the graduation?
-A nuclear power station? Air traffic?
-Yeah...
With a virus like that already planted,
he can knock out just about anything.
Hi!
-What's that?
-Champagne.
Well, sparkling wine, but same idea.
We're celebrating.
-Where's the law book?
-I cleaned up. In the bookcase.
Hey... Today is
our eight-month anniversary.
-We didn't celebrate seven.
-We didn't live together then.
So we're celebrating every month now?
-You don't think it's worth celebrating?
-Sure. Yes.
-Cheers.
-Cheers!
All done. Thank you.
-What are you doing?
-I need to work.
-But you just got back from work.
-I know.
I thought we could do
something together.
-Maybe go out to dinner?
-I ate on the way back.
-When do you think you'll be done?
-I don't know.
-You want some coffee?
-No, thanks.
Maybe we can watch a movie later.
I need to work.
Thank you for the sparkling wine.
-Working late?
-Yes.
Me, too.
You have to,
or you don't want to go home?
Well... A little bit of both,
I guess. Yourself?
Living together
is harder than I thought.
You have to give and take,
and every relationship...
The leaked propylene oxide
contaminated the drinking water.
-Yeah, I heard.
-They've been pro-environment so far.
Poisoning the water
doesn't fit the pattern.
Maybe they protested the location,
and the consequences were unintended.
They must have known
the water would get contaminated.
-Any idea what the graduation might be?
-No.
John is going through Madsen's clients.
I'll try to ID more boat corpses.
So you'll be here a while? Me, too.
Hey.
-He's slept for a few hours.
-OK.
The doctor says he can go home
in a couple of days.
That's great. Poor little thing.
-What are you reading?
-An old suicide case file.
-Saga's sister.
-Why? Is there something odd there?
No, I was just curious.
Saga's mom had Munchausen.
That's why Saga's sister
was living with her.
They found out
when she was ten years old.
The sister? What about Saga?
Was she a victim, too?
It doesn't say that she was.
And she won't talk about her family.
She talks about everything else,
so maybe she didn't want you to know.
Yeah, that's what Pernille said.
-Who is Pernille?
-A colleague.
She's working on the case, too.
From Copenhagen.
And that's all there is to it.
I'll sleep at your place.
Yes, do that.
-Bye, bye.
-Bye.
Well... Doesn't really make that big
of a difference shooting it yourself.
I wrote a draft of my speech
for the EU summit.
-Could you read it later?
-Sure. I'd love to.
I want to make sure
everyone will get it.
-Are you speaking at the EU summit?
-Oliver didn't tell you?
-That's fantastic. Congratulations.
-Thanks.
I spoke to the woman
who's writing your book.
Right, Bodil.
You were brutally honest, I take it?
I mean, it's a testament. Or a tribute.
I know how much it means to Oliver.
So if it didn't mean so much to him,
you'd talk trash about me?
No, that's not what I meant.
-You twist everything.
-It could be construed that way.
Well, that's not what I meant.
I'm sorry.
Thanks for dinner, it was good.
-Are you going to make it home OK?
-Across the street? I think so.
I'm going to take a bath, then to bed.
I've got an early meeting. Bye.
-Bye. Thanks for a nice evening.
-Thanks.
Is it just not possible for you
to say no to her?
What?
She poisons the whole evening
and you just sit there.
I didn't notice.
I'm going to bed. Are you coming?
After I send out some work emails
and clean up in the kitchen.
-OK. Good night.
-Good night.
-Jens won't be coming today.
-Why not?
-He's not feeling so well, he said.
-Is that what he said?
Are you sick?
Did I tell you that Nikolaj was sick?
Munchausen by proxy. Heard of it?
His nanny poisoned him
with blood pressure medication.
Saga found out.
Sure, he wasn't supposed to die,
but this time... she did save him.
Here, I brought you coffee.
Or you got an upset stomach?
-Is it?
-No, it's not a stomach thing.
I wish someone had been on the bridge
when Mikaela crashed.
Someone that could've saved your son.
I want you to leave.
Yes. I can tell.
We've ID'd one,
maybe two more from the boat.
-When did you do that?
-Last night.
-I was going to do it this morning.
-What?
-Right, but I did it last night.
Lars Munk-Andersen,
33 years old, from Copenhagen.
Was identified through a dental bridge.
Roger Bengtzon, 22 years old.
He worked with Karin Miller.
Reported missing at the same time.
The police speculated
they were staying away together.
But they weren't.
Pernille, go talk to
Lars Munk-Andersen's relatives.
Roger Bengtzon's brother
is on his way here.
-I'll go to my desk and...
-Go through all missing persons.
Crosscheck forensic reports
for any links you may have missed.
Sure thing. Thanks.
-Bye.
-Bye, bye.
-Roger...
-Roger.
-No, it's Roger Bengtzon.
That pronunciation is American
or English. In Swedish it's Roger.
No way! OK. Roger...
I wanted to think he was on some beach
in Thailand or wherever.
That he'd just said, fuck it all.
Had your brother mentioned
that he had problems or felt threatened?
No, nothing like that.
Does the name Marcus Stenberg
mean anything to you?
No.
Roger worked in eldercare
with Karin Miller.
-Among other things.
-What else did he do?
What didn't he do?
Gambling, poker... clinical trials...
...art school model, porn.
-Always needing money.
-Did he owe anyone?
No, nothing like that.
And no drugs or any shit like that.
-Porn?
-Yes.
-Did your daughter do porn?
-Beg your pardon?
Did your daughter do porn?
Did she have sex on film?
No, she did not.
-Are you sure?
-Yes, I am.
It's a strange question,
but would you know if she did?
Why are you asking?
She had breast implants,
like many in that business.
-It explains how she afforded it.
-You didn't know her.
-No.
-You didn't know Karin.
-Like I said, no.
-She didn't do that kind of stuff.
-She didn't do any...porn.
-No?
-Anything else?
-No.
Sorry to have disturbed you.
Next time you ask if someone's daughter
has done porn, be more gentle.
It's highly unlikely
there'll be a next time.
Well, if there is a next time.
-It's got to be hopeless.
-Yeah, you know what she's like...
Munk-Andersen was married
with two children.
The wife is sure he wasn't in porn.
Wait, how is porn related to
social injustice and the environment?
Many believe porn
and trafficking are linked.
Have you ID'd any more
from the boat?
Not yet. One had an injured foot.
We're crosschecking hospital records.
The others, we may never
find out who they were.
-Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
-Sammy Nyrop.
-We talked about the barrels.
-Yes. What do you want?
I got another text
about picking up a barrel.
-What do I do?
-Do nothing.
Await my instructions.
I'll call you back.
He can't know we found Julian,
or he wouldn't use Sammy again.
-I bet Ramon's in the barrel.
-We don't know that.
-What about the barrel?
-Let Sammy pick it up.
He'll get a text about payment.
We may be able to trace it.
It's our only connection
to Mother Of Three.
Do you know who it is?
-Why do you ask?
-For no reason.
We need your phone.
He'll text you about payment.
We may be able to trace it.
-I'll be back later.
-OK.
-So...your head still hurts?
-No, they gave me a pill.
When's the police coming? Wouldn't
they think it's important I remembered?
OK, promise you won't get mad at me.
-I never called them.
-Why not?
Because last time
their behavior was inexcusable.
-They shouldn't treat you that way.
-But I can give them a description!
They'll have to work it out without you.
Ask them to get here - now!
OK.
-I want other people to talk to Laura.
-But Norén and Rohde are in charge.
I don't give a shit.
I don't want them near her again.
Fine. I'll send someone else
with a composite artist.
-Great. Thank you.
-As soon as possible.
Rasmus, Laura Möllberg remembers
her shooter. Can you get on that?
Absolutely.
Sammy Nyrop's phone.
He'll get a text about payment.
OK. I'll prep the tracing.
You have a visitor.
-Hello.
-What do you want?
I got upset.
Last time you were at my house.
-That was not our intention.
-Well, I did.
So I wanted to show you...
...try to prove to you
that Karin didn't do any of...that.
Any porn?
So I went through her stuff.
I thought you cleaned everything out.
Yes, her room, but we still
had a box left in the attic.
And I found this.
Payment for participation
in a clinical trial.
If she did that, maybe it would prove
she did have the money.
-See where it's from?
-Medisonus.
That's where Niklas Svensson worked.
-Yes, Peter?
-I did a routine check.
I do them regularly,
especially after Niklas Svensson.
Mikkel Höst has used his access card
in a few different places.
-Often at night.
-Who's Mikkel Höst?
There is no employee with that name.
He was in the research department.
That's why I'm telling you.
OK.
He got a text.
-Can you find it?
-It's still turned on.
Still turned on...
Now it's off. But I got some info.
-That's as close as I get.
-It's in Hvidovre.
Medisonus is in Hvidovre.
Hi.
-Hey. Rasmus Larsson.
-Right, hello.
Where's Laura?
-Physical therapy. For her shoulder.
-Wait here.
What the fuck?
Move!
Move! Move! Police!
Laura! Where's Laura?
Goddamn it...
Fuck... Goddamn it!
Subtitles: Mario Bernengo
TC:subtitling
Edited by thedude95