A woman has died
from a poisoned apple.
Negative human impact
on the environment - hence the symbol.
So this is a pathos-driven
eco-terrorism of sorts?
The man who died. You read about it.
I'm chasing a new keynote speaker.
The guy we got ruined my birthday
by getting poisoned and dying.
-It's...new boobs.
-You want me to get bigger boobs?
-What's this?
-For when you need really great sex.
-Where are you going?
-With you.
-No. You're staying here.
-OK...
-Where are you going?
-I'm heading out.
Rasmus Larsson, Malmö Police...
-Where have you been all day?
-The ER.
I had a sandwich that contained nuts.
I've got a bad nut allergy.
Axel Möllberg.
I've got some footage for you.
-You saw where it headed?
-I kept shooting my daughter.
-I can take her job.
-Top students don't take gap years.
-What did you get yourself into?
-Do I get the job or not?
You know how everything works?
I want to see Jens in prison.
One day you just felt so great
you decided to see your son's murderer?
What was that harbor thing?
-Any word?
-They should be pleased.
We're meeting
some higher-ups tonight.
Hey. I love you, Linus.
It's all going to be fine.
-Linus just made a call.
-We're assuming to Niklas.
EPISODE 4
Is it them?
Mads Nielsen... Niklas Svensson...
She looks like the girl from the grocery
store pictures. Her, we don't know.
-It's the four from the videos.
-Probably.
-That one's the pig.
-How do you know?
The scar on the wrist.
Suicide.
Why do it here?
They must've known they'd get caught,
given the scope of our raid.
It's not uncommon with these groups.
It's preferable to getting caught.
Thanks, I got it.
Hi, Linus. I'm Rasmus. I thought
we'd go and sit down in here.
You want anything?
Like a sandwich, or a soda?
-Why am I here?
-We just want to talk to you.
I don't know where Niklas is.
Honestly, I don't know.
Right... So it's just you
and your brother?
Why are you asking me that?
Did you get him?
-Is he here? Can I see him?
-No... Hey, let's get something to eat.
Let's get a soda or something.
Do you have any change
for the vending machine?
...whether it's the same four
individuals in animal masks
claiming responsibility for recent
attacks, has not yet been verified.
-How many people are there?
-Four people.
-Have you identified them?
-No, but it's two men and two women.
We think they're involved
in the harbor explosion.
How did they kill themselves?
Some kind of poison.
That's all we know presently.
We heard they killed themselves
when the police came.
I can't speak to that.
-Did they feel cornered by the police?
-I don't want to speculate.
-Did they leave a message?
-No comment...
Linus!
Hey...
I'm sorry.
Police have thus far
not named the victims.
We don't know how they
ended up in the container.
We believe it's four people -
two men and two women.
Yes, it's four people. We have not
yet been able to make a positive ID.
We believe these people
are connected to the recent attacks.
Evidence suggests use of poison,
but it's too early to say.
-Could it be a mass suicide?
-I can't comment on that.
Hello? Who is this?
Julian. Mathilde's brother.
Who are you?
This is Martin Rohde,
Copenhagen Police.
I'd like to talk to you about
your sister. Where are you?
I'm at home. What's this about?
Is Mathilde there?
-Where do you live?
-52 Aksel Heides Gade.
-I'll be there in 30 minutes.
-OK...
This is where police this morning
found four bodies in a container.
There is a flurry of activity here,
with both Swedish and Danish police...
-Is this your sister?
-Yes. That's Mathilde.
-Are you positive?
-Yes, I...
Yes.
She was supposed to be here
for breakfast. She's always broke.
-Were you close?
-Yes, in a way.
We liked seeing each other,
but led very different lives.
-Did she really like you?
-What do you mean by that?
You seem to represent
everything she opposed.
As I said, we led different lives.
-Did you have friends in common?
-No.
-Did she ever talk about her friends?
-Yes, sometimes.
Did she mention any names?
There was a Swedish girl.
Her name might have been Kattis.
-I think she was dating a Mads...
-Mads Nielsen?
-Yes, I think that was his name.
-Any other names?
-Not that I can think of.
-When did you last see her?
Yesterday. At our father's.
We have lunch once a week.
-How did she seem?
-Normal.
-Could you sit down?
-Why?
-I don't care for your pacing.
-I'm not touching anything.
No, but it's...
OK.
It's almost as if
you don't want people to like you.
You've lost a sister. Imagine to be told
she probably didn't like you.
-But she didn't like me.
-Didn't you live together?
Yes. She liked me better than our
parents and was too young to live alone.
-Was she like you?
-No, she was normal.
Rather popular. That's why people were
so surprised when she killed herself.
-We hope you'll do it.
-I'm here because Boris was poisoned.
If you wanted me so badly,
why wasn't I your first choice?
No particular reason. You're both
highly sought-after speakers.
You're both well-respected
within your respective fields.
-We could only hire one of you.
-I'd be delighted to do it.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
-What happens now?
-A lot.
I'm sure, but what do I need to do?
Right now, we need the title
and an outline of your speech.
-For when?
-Yesterday. It's for the program.
What was Boris' speech about?
It was called
"Local actions, global challenges."
Seriously? That could be anything.
You know what? Keep it in.
-Are you sure?
-No one really listens, anyway.
Katarina Lövgren, age 24,
Swedish, single.
Mathilde Madsen, age 25, Danish, single.
Copenhagen residents. That's it for now.
We're profiling them,
talking to relatives and friends...
I want computers,
phones, diaries - everything.
-Diaries?
-Twitter, Facebook, Instagram, blogs...
Have we ruled out suicide?
I mean, what's the motive?
They were liabilities.
We'd ID'd two of them.
A network disposes of those
who threaten to expose it.
Until further notice,
this is a murder investigation.
-Where are you going?
-Tell Linus Svensson about his brother.
Um... Linus knows Niklas is dead.
-Why did you tell him?
-I didn't, he saw it on TV.
-Why was he watching TV?
-That was my bad. That's on me.
-But he knows.
-Yes, that was stupid.
Yep...
Hi...
-Andrea Melin, social services.
-Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
-Do you know how long this will take?
-No.
I'm about to show you some pictures.
Tell me if it's your brother.
-Excuse me, is this necessary?
-Yes.
Linus, is this your brother
Niklas Svensson?
I want you to say it and point him out.
-That's my brother.
-Great. Thanks.
-It's my fault.
-What's your fault?
You found him because
I called him, didn't you?
Yes.
-Are we done here?
-No. We also need to question him.
Linus, did you know
what your brother was doing?
I don't mean being a lab technician,
I mean the other stuff - the attacks.
Tell them as much as you know.
You're not accused of anything.
Not for the time being.
Did you know what he was doing?
Do you know who
he was doing it with?
Where was he
when he wasn't at home?
Did your brother have a lot of friends?
Did you get a lot of visitors at home?
No.
Let's take a break. If you think
of anything, tell Andrea here.
She can then tell us. OK?
We did get one... Yesterday.
-One what?
-Visitor, at home.
-Outside.
-Did you know him?
They met outside.
I saw them from the balcony.
-What did he look like?
-Like...normal.
-Was it him?
-No.
Anything special about him?
Hair? Beard? Tattoos?
What if I've done something illegal?
Would I go to jail?
-No, you're too young.
-Juvenile detention, maybe.
You won't go to jail, I promise you.
Just tell me what happened.
-I tagged his car.
-You put your signature on his car?
-On the one side.
-What kind of car?
I don't know. It was light...metallic.
Can you draw what you did here?
Denmark sent their files.
You want Katarina or Mathilde?
-Katarina.
-I'll email you everything.
THE MAN...
...AGE 30-35...
BLACK JACKET
BLUE JACKET
There's this witness, a neighbor
looking through the peephole...
A man was assaulted outside
Katarina's door the day she died.
-It needs to go on the wall.
-Sure.
Tell all units in Sweden and Denmark
to look for a car with that tag.
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
Rasmus, call all the body shops.
If it was my car, I'd get that fixed.
-Absolutely.
-Martin?
Cheers.
It's what I always say, problems are
there for us to celebrate a solution.
-Viktoria. I couldn't figure her out.
-What's to figure out?
She's giving a lecture,
you're not moving in together.
Alexander actually got me
something else last night. A boob job.
-Breast implants.
-You're lying.
Caroline! I'm sorry!
This completely changes
my opinion of Alexander.
-He knows exactly what a woman wants.
-He does?
Someone offers me a lift, I get down
on my knees and thank him.
-Bodil...
-Things only go one way, that's down.
It was the most
humiliating experience of my life.
He said it was for me,
because I'd been griping about it.
I've been griping about the sunshade.
He's done nothing about that.
Of course it's for him.
Isn't a little spark worth it?
It shouldn't be necessary.
-Did you call that number?
-Stop it.
-It's someone who loves you for you.
-It's someone who wants to bang me.
And to flirt with you!
And to lust for you!
And to give it to you good!
Everything Alexander can't give you.
-You're not coming in?
-No, this is your department.
I'm calling home.
Nikolaj fell ill last night.
Saga?
My son Nikolaj fell ill last night.
Right, I hope he feels better today.
Go be with your dead bodies.
Did they kill themselves?
They all had traces
of an ampoule in their mouths.
One ampoule kills within seconds.
The poison is identical to the one
injected in the groceries.
This is the first victim
of the poisoned groceries.
This one is from the container.
Their symptoms are almost identical,
but tiny differences can be spotted.
Pinkish hue.
Greenish livor mortis
suggests cyanide poisoning.
Traces of foaming mucus
at the mouth from hyperventilating...
...due to reduced oxygen uptake.
No signs of struggle from
having been force-fed the poison.
Identical symptoms.
She's got a higher concentration
of cyanide in the skin.
And traces in the mucous membrane.
"Swellings and bruises on her hand
above the little finger."
She was pounding hard on the wall,
struggling to get out.
It took time. More time
than an ampoule would have taken.
-She was gassed.
-Yes.
I was almost starting to get worried.
-Is this a good time?
-Sure.
I got the pictures.
-Which one do you like?
-They're all good.
-Were they taken before the...?
-No, they're all new.
This is the best one.
Thank you, Dharma.
-Do you want to close the door?
-Of course.
Hi, is this Claudio? Hello.
My name is Caroline.
My sister Bodil gave me your number.
Close the door.
We can rule out suicide.
They died from inhaling palytoxin.
-They were gassed?
-Yes.
They were locked in,
and gas was pumped in.
The killer aired out the gas,
positioned the bodies and wrote a sign.
-Why isn't Linus in a foster home yet?
-They're doing the paperwork now.
You said before you thought it was
your fault your brother died. Why?
-I was the one who called him.
-Yes?
On TV, they said they died
because you guys were coming.
You said you went there
because of my phone call.
They didn't commit suicide.
They were murdered.
Your call made no difference.
They would have died either way.
So it wasn't your fault.
So blaming yourself is just dumb.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
-Saga, take a look at this. That guy.
-Who's that?
A man who was assaulted in Katarina's
building a few hours before her death.
-By who?
-Two women.
Katarina and possibly Mathilde.
Check any assault charges
brought that day.
Five, nine, seven, fifteen.
I found it. I found the car.
An auto paint shop in Brønshøj took in
a champagne-colored Audi A7 Quattro.
Tagged on one side.
Registration number is TS59715.
-John?
-Hang on, hang on...
Belongs to a Julian Madsen. Isn't that
the same last name as Mathilde?
For fuck's sake, that's her brother.
To be sent within a week...
I'm going to call you back.
Copenhagen Police.
Is Julian Madsen here?
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
Where is his office?
There, but he hasn't come in today.
This is a warrant to seize computers,
servers, hard drives - everything.
-You know where we can reach him?
-No...
-Have you tried him at home?
-Yeah...
-When did you last see him?
-Yesterday afternoon.
What do you want him for?
Do you manage Julian's calendar?
No, I'm not his secretary.
He manages his own.
-Did you take his car to the body shop?
-He asked me. He's my boss.
And now you don't know where he is?
Call me as soon as you hear from him.
-You realize it's important?
-Absolutely.
Age 31, studied at the IT University
and MIT in Massachusetts.
18 employees. Last year's turnover
was 83 million kroner.
How's a guy like that
involved in this?
Martin! A word?
How are you?
-What the fuck do you mean by that?
-I talked to Niels.
-You really want to keep seeing Jens?
-Why? Niels doesn't want me to?
-He struggles to see the point.
-After one week?
Is it really helping, Martin?
It will. I know it will.
-We're going by Mette.
-Why?
-To see Nikolaj.
-But he's sick?
Yes, that's why.
-This is where she lives?
-Yes.
-The last one was much nicer.
-Mette thinks so, too.
Hello?
-Hi! I thought I heard something.
-This is Simon and Sanne.
Simon and Sanne, this is Saga Norén,
Malmö County Police.
This is Anna-Dea.
We couldn't cope without her.
Hey, champ.
Hi... How are you doing?
-OK.
-Is it boring, being sick?
-You reading this one?
-Yes, Anna-Dea reads it to me.
-Should I read it to you?
-Please.
All right, scooch over.
Go on. Here we go, sit up...
Aren't they adorable? I love kids.
-Why?
-Because they're kids.
They're just lovely. And I'm
sort of an extra mom to them.
Martin's gone and Mette works a lot.
I don't know what they'd do without me.
-Get another nanny.
-It's not that simple.
Why? Are you specially trained?
No. But you heard what Martin said,
they couldn't cope without me.
He didn't mean you specifically,
he meant the services you provide.
You're replaceable.
Shall we go? He's asleep.
He drifted off when I started reading.
I'll check on him later
and give him something to drink.
-You're the best, you know that?
-Thanks.
-Laura...
-Fuck!
You scared the shit out of me.
-Are they still there?
-No, but they took a bunch of stuff.
Computers, servers...
-What the hell did you do?
-I can't tell you, but I'm fucked.
I need your help.
I didn't know who else to ask.
One of the cops gave me his card.
I promised to call him
in case you got in touch.
-You get 5,000 kroner if you help me.
-With what?
First, to get me out of here.
Then I need a computer.
-What did you do?
-10,000 kroner, no more questions.
Deal?
Yes.
-You've got a lovely home.
-Thank you.
-Have you lived here long?
-Yes, seven years. If that's long.
-Do you like it here?
-I do, very much.
There's not going to be a husband
coming home all of a sudden?
No, no! He's away on business, so...
No need to explain.
Just wanted to make sure.
You want something to drink?
Water? Coffee? Wine?
No. Thanks, though.
-Maybe one glass of wine.
-OK.
-Thank you. Cheers, Caroline.
-Cheers.
It could be more chilled.
I think I've got one that's...
Caroline. It tastes fine.
It's fine.
Listen...
We won't do anything
you don't want to do.
OK?
You're in charge.
Unless you really want me
to take charge.
Yeah? OK.
No! No, I can't.
I can't do it. I just can't.
I think you should go.
I'm really sorry.
Maybe you just need
a little more convincing.
No...
You want me in charge, right?
Yeah, you want me in charge.
No, don't!
I'm going to have to ask you to leave.
I don't know how payment works...?
-Right, it's 1,500 kroner.
-1,500 kroner?
ALARM DEACTIVATED
You've got her picture on your desk.
How do you know her?
The deal was no questions.
She was my sister. Mathilde.
-And she's dead?
-She was murdered last night.
-The police thought you did it?
-It's complicated, but it wasn't me.
-So who was it?
-I don't know. Yet.
-Any of those cams work?
-Yes, why?
I'm meeting someone tonight.
You film it, you get another 5,000.
-Why not go to the police?
-Forget it, I shouldn't have asked you.
What was I thinking?
Thank you for your help.
Wait.
Let's call it a night.
We'll pick it up tomorrow.
-Can I ride with you?
-Of course.
-You don't have a car?
-No.
Bye, Saga.
Well, thank you for the ride.
No problem at all.
No need to thank me every time.
-OK. Have a great evening.
-You, too.
-See you tomorrow.
-Yes.
No, I'm sorry. Sorry.
It's OK.
-You don't want to come up?
-I can't.
OK.
-See you tomorrow.
-Yep.
I saw you and Lillian on TV today.
Interesting case.
I've been following it in the papers.
I was just wondering,
why do they use a frog as a symbol?
All right. What do you want
to talk about? Mette? The kids?
-August?
-Saga asked about you.
-Today?
-No, a year ago, while chasing you.
I told her it couldn't be you.
That you weren't that type of person.
You were mistaken.
All that single-minded anger.
The focus you had.
That can't be you. It was some other
Jens who killed all those people.
The Jens I knew, where did he go?
He died. You got in bed with his wife
and killed his son.
You know what I think? I think you're
fighting to keep the old Jens at bay.
Sounds exciting. Are you trying
to say I'm a schizophrenic?
I'm trying to say you're human.
That you're in there, I can see it.
And I want to try to talk to you.
I decide if we meet or not.
I'll see you, then.
-Say hi to Mette.
-Will do.
-Hi there.
-How did you get in?
-Your colleagues let me in.
-Sloppy. They don't know you.
I brought food.
I thought you'd be hungry.
Yes.
You get to choose between chicken
and... This is chicken, too.
OK, you don't get to choose.
-What are you doing?
-Working.
What are you working on?
What's all this?
I'm examining evidence we seized
for anything that might help our case.
What's this?
It's a list.
I don't know... Put it back.
You need to go.
-I just got here.
-I need to focus.
-I can't focus if you're here.
-You keep thinking about my body?
No, because you're a disruption.
And they say romance is dead...
What do you mean?
-Was it any good?
-Yeah...
-I need to show you something.
-You need to go.
Here. Leave the same way you came.
Julian's phone company
sent through his records.
Here, he got a text at 3.18 p.m.
Then he turned off his phone.
It came from this number.
A Laura Möllberg.
His receptionist. She tipped him off.
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
Laura Möllberg?
She's not home.
-We know each other.
-Yes.
-I showed you the footage of the boat.
-The ship. I know.
-You recognize him?
-Yes. He was here this afternoon.
They've been here. A camera's missing
and Laura had used the computer.
How does your daughter know
Julian Madsen?
She works for him.
I don't know in what capacity.
Did they say where they were going?
I don't know, I wasn't home then.
I saw them on the home security system.
-Call her.
-I've tried numerous times. It's off.
They used the computer,
so we'll take it with us.
OK...
That's where we're meeting.
Try to find a vantage point.
Just shoot whatever happens.
Try to get our faces on camera. OK?
OK.
-We're up. What do you want to see?
-The latest activity.
The first thing is a visit to a site
called "Children and Parents".
Someone logged in with the handle
"Stressed Out Dad" at 6.29 p.m.
and chatted with someone
called "Mother Of Three."
Just one message sent. "D. 10 p.m."
10 p.m., sure. But D?
-What have you got?
-Come on.
Look at this. A letter, and coordinates.
Latitude and longitude, put together.
-It's this location...at 10 p.m.
-One second.
Malmö Stadium.
Set up a perimeter,
and make sure no one gets in or out.
No, no, no!
Come on, come on!
Come on...
Come on!
Martin here.
They just hung up.
I don't recognize the number.
Hi, it's Laura,
I can't take your call right now...
There!
She's been shot.
-This one's locked.
-Watch out.
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
Send an ambulance to Malmö Stadium.
-Is she breathing?
-Yes!
-Find anything?
-No camera in the car.
-Julian probably took it.
-Why would he want to shoot Laura?
-He doesn't need her anymore.
-He was meeting someone here.
-Why bring a camera to a meeting?
-To record it.
So she needs to be hidden,
but also get good footage.
Up on the roof there.
-Right here, right?
-Yes.
There it is.
The memory card is missing.
It's right here.
That's perfect.
Oh, hey.
-I'm sorry if I woke you.
-No, I was waiting for you.
-You're a bit late.
-The flight was delayed.
Really? I checked online.
It said it had landed on time.
Well, it didn't.
-Who was here?
-No one.
Because I saw two wine glasses
in the kitchen.
That was just Bodil, she stopped by.
-Oh, Bodil. That must have been nice.
-Yes, it was.
-Get in.
-I'm tired. Can't we just go to sleep?
-Yes. Of course.
-Good night, honey.
-Any news from the hospital?
-Nothing yet.
John checked the chat.
Julian was just a middle man.
He didn't know his sister's group
would get murdered.
-Can you trace "Mother Of Three"?
-Not yet.
But they discussed
a "birthday party" and a "graduation."
-After the group was killed?
-Yes. There are more of them.
Subtitles: Mario Bernengo
TC:subtitling
Edited by thedude95