So that's what we're dealing with?
A pathos-driven eco-terrorism of sorts?
They've discussed a "birthday party"
and "graduation."
Romstock started its production
exactly three years ago today.
So the question is,
what's the graduation?
Our only leads are
Medisonus and Mother Of Three.
Our head of security
found a forged access card.
Mikkel Höst has used his card
several times over the last few months.
Very often after normal work hours.
-And you never employed a Mikkel Höst?
-Never.
CEO and majority owner
is Viktoria Nordgren.
-I'd never allow...
-...anything to stand in my way.
-I thought you'd be home late.
-It is late.
Police! Freeze!
Peter Thaulov is not
on Medisonus' payroll.
But he does handle security
for Medisonus and other firms.
One is Copenhagen IT Consulting.
Helga Blomgren travels to Thailand
a lot. She has her mail forwarded.
Lennart Blomgren. He's alive.
Someone logged in
with the handle "Mother Of Three."
-What do you know about Mother Of Three?
-Mother Of Three? Nothing. Who is that?
I saw the guy who shot me -
in my dream! Call the police!
Yes, that's it. That's him.
EPISODE 9
-Looks nothing like Peter Thaulov.
-No, it doesn't.
Whoever shot Laura
must be Mother Of Three.
Hence Peter Thaulov
is not Mother Of Three.
-He could still be Mikkel Höst.
-And he could still ID this person.
He looks familiar,
but I can't place him.
We've searched your home and office.
-What...did you tell my wife?
-We found this at your office.
A Medisonus access card
issued to Mikkel Höst.
-Hang on, that can't be right.
-Yes.
In that case it was planted there.
Someone's trying to frame me.
I alerted you to Mikkel Höst.
Would I have done that if it was me?
Gertrud Kofoed told us about him.
You answered questions.
I thought it was about something else.
It has nothing to do with me.
-Who knows about Höst?
-Many people.
I told Medisonus' management,
my bosses at FRIM,
my co-workers at Medisonus
who need to know...
-How many people is that?
-About 20.
And who among those 20 people
is trying to frame you?
-How's it going?
-Good.
I'm almost done. You want some coffee?
No, thank you. Does that mean you'll
be spending less time in the basement?
What's that supposed to mean?
Exactly that. You're down there
in front of your computer a lot.
I'm working.
Sometimes it seems
you'd rather be there than with me.
How's Viktoria today?
I don't know, I haven't seen her.
Why? Is she not feeling well?
Did she tell you something?
-No. Maybe you'd seen her, is all.
-No.
Nothing.
How long can we keep this photo?
48 hours.
What the hell are you doing here?
-I've got something.
-You're off the case.
This is from Ängby
high school 1988-1989.
That's Viktoria Nordgren. Weren't you
looking into Medisonus when I left?
-You didn't leave, you were reassigned.
-You looked into Medisonus. So did I.
Check out the back row,
in the middle - number six.
-Marcus Stenberg.
-They know each other.
He's shown up three times in this case.
He was a classmate of Medisonus' CEO.
-You think that's a coincidence?
-That's unlikely.
Thanks.
-I don't suppose there's a chance...?
-No. Not a chance.
Right... Right, OK.
-I've stopped seeing Jens.
-I told you it would be useless.
But it wasn't. I got to him.
-You got to him?
-To the old Jens. I got to him.
-Did he ask for forgiveness?
-No, but there's no need.
I could see it in his eyes.
-And that's enough for you?
-Yes.
That's enough for me, because now I'm
free of him. He's not in here anymore.
And that's enough for me, Saga.
-What do you want this time?
-Her.
-Viktoria. What about her?
-You remember her?
Yeah, we dated a couple of months
our senior year. Why?
-Have you seen her lately?
-Not since high school.
-Any reason she'd have it in for you?
-After 25 years? No.
What about when you were dating?
Any problems from back then?
No, like what?
Rape, sexual exploitation,
physical or psychological abuse.
What do you think of me?
Nothing. But violence is
not uncommon in close relationships.
OK... So you think she's somehow
involved in what's been going on?
-Do you?
-No.
Do you recognize this person?
No, sorry.
-If you think of anything...
-I'll call. I know the drill.
-What did Stenberg say?
-Nothing, really.
Thai police apprehended
Lennart Blomgren.
John is working out the technical kinks
so you can question him.
You should be all set.
Lennart, can you hear us?
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
This is Martin Rohde, Copenhagen Police.
We need to ask you about seven bodies.
At least three were involved in a trial
at Medisonus in 2002-2003
when you were head of research.
Why are you hiding out in Thailand?
What do you want to know?
Tell us about the trials.
It was for a drug that was meant
to mitigate effects of any intolerance.
Gluten, lactose... The new, widespread
afflictions of Western society.
And what happened?
We'd just begun trials when we learned
our competitor was doing the same thing.
So they asked me to move things along.
So you skipped several steps
in the research?
We went from unfinished animal testing
straight to phase-one trials.
Seven subjects.
Later on the animals
exhibited severe side effects.
-I contacted management.
-Who was in management?
I reported only to our global
R&D director in Germany.
-What was his or her name?
-Pascal Brennan.
Then what?
They wanted me to destroy
everything to do with the trials.
And I...did as they said.
What happened to the subjects?
Pascal got their personal information
and told me I couldn't contact them.
-Did you try to contact them anyway?
-Later on...
But they had disappeared.
They had all disappeared.
-I got scared, so I disappeared, too.
-Pascal Brennan, 2005.
SCIENTIST DIES IN SINGLE-CAR ACCIDENT
Pascal Brennan Is Dead
-What happens to me now?
-This interrogation is over.
Who were on the board ten years ago?
We'll find out, but Viktoria Nordgren
was already CEO.
Viktoria Nordgren, Medisonus.
Connections to the case?
We know there's a connection
between Nordgren and Stenberg.
Three of the seven in the motorboat
are connected. The rest, too, probably.
The text to Sammy Nyrop came from
the area where Medisonus is located.
The plague bacteria and the poison
are also most likely from Medisonus.
Romstock, the company
with the leak of propyl...
-Propylene oxide.
-Right.
Romstock supplies chemicals to Philbs
& Son, Medisonus' biggest competitor.
The attack on Romstock
halted their production for weeks.
We still don't know
what the "graduation" is.
Viktoria is speaking
at the EU summit this week.
Speaking at the EU summit? I've heard
that, in connection with someone else.
What are you thinking?
Boris Williams - the poisoned-meat guy.
He'd been announced
as a speaker at the EU summit.
Rasmus didn't find a toad
where it was bought.
His place was broken into
two days before he died.
How did we miss that connection?
Maybe the meat
was poisoned in his home?
That explains why there was no toad.
At 3 p.m.
it's Viktoria Nordgren's speech:
"Local commitment, global results."
-Caroline Brandstrup.
-Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
-We spoke the other day.
-I know, but I'm busy now.
Boris Williams was to speak
at the EU summit.
-Right, but he's dead.
-I know.
But why was he replaced
by Viktoria Nordgren?
It was always going to be
one of the two.
So Viktoria Nordgren was
the only possible candidate?
Yes. Why do you ask? Hello?
That was Lillian. She got a warrant
to search Viktoria Nordgren's place.
She has cancer.
She only has six months to live.
-Why is that important?
-No way she could do all that.
So we assume she's not alone.
Laura's shooter was a man.
-Is she married?
-No. But she has a brother.
Can you get a picture of him, John?
This is him right here.
I'll be damned.
Send us his address.
-Hello?
-Where are you?
-At home.
-Come over.
-What's up? Did something happen?
-Come over now.
-Who was that?
-Viktoria.
She wanted me to come over.
And you certainly don't mind.
Pernille, you're on speaker.
Medisonus' stock rose 6.8 points
after the plague broke out.
Does Oliver work at Medisonus?
No, but between the Nordgren siblings
they control almost 50 percent of shares.
What did they make off the outbreak?
The value of Viktoria's shares rose
by 200 million kroner.
-Viktoria?
-In here.
Hi.
Sit down.
-How are you?
-Sit.
I saw Bodil today.
Enough already.
-You stop meddling in my life.
-I just wanted to help...
I don't give a shit what you wanted!
You think I need you.
I don't. I never did.
I've tolerated having you
running around me,
buying a house
30 yards away from mine...
That you're here seeking validation
every ten fucking minutes,
and never showed the slightest hint
of any talent or initiative.
You're useless.
And my life is literally too short
to have useless people around me.
-I've only tried to...
-Yes!
You've tried. But it hasn't
worked out all that great, has it?
-Sorry, I...
-Cut it out!
-Leave the keys and get out of here.
-The keys...?
Put the keys on the table and leave.
I decide if and when
you enter this house again.
Viktoria.
What?
You said I never showed
any talent or initiative.
That I'm useless.
You have no idea what I've done for you.
I was the one who spread the plague.
What are you talking about?
I had those kids infected
and had the boat run aground.
Our stock shot up almost seven points.
How do you think you got
that EU summit job?
-Boris died.
-Exactly.
I've always been there for you.
The side effects of the intolerance drug
could have ruined us.
-I dealt with that, too.
-What do you mean?
I sank them
in Marcus Stenberg's motorboat.
Remember Marcus?
Who knocked you up in high school?
He broke up after your abortion.
He had it coming, like all those who
try to get away with mistreating you.
Like that little Claudissimio of yours.
He wanted to write a book
about all the people he'd fucked.
I want everyone to respect you
the way I respect you.
The way I love you, Viktoria.
They need to see how amazing you are.
People are so easily forgotten.
But I'll make sure everyone
remembers you and what you've done.
-Oliver...
-My finale will make you immortal.
-You're going to save Europe.
-Oliver, hear me out...
-It's too late.
-The wheels are in motion.
-Go to the cops.
I know you wouldn't want this,
but that's impossible.
Everyone knows you're ill. You'll be
a saint, who died quietly in her sleep.
No... Oliver!
No...
Oliver!
-The doors are open in both houses.
-Wait here.
-What's our play?
-You take Oliver's house. Martin, come.
Copenhagen Police!
Just go in.
Hans, you'd better come over here. Now.
-So your brother was trying to kill you?
-Yes. Suffocate me with a pillow.
Then your sister-in-law
comes to the rescue?
Yes.
I don't remember what happened...
Saga?
This was found in one of his drawers.
Is it the same poison from the food?
Palytoxin.
-Did you know he kept this at home?
-No.
She has great timing,
your sister-in-law.
And Oliver confessed
to all this before he died?
You don't believe me.
Your sister-in-law
has good timing, is all.
How did Gertrud know you were in danger?
I don't know.
-Why were you at Viktoria's?
-He was trying to kill her...
-I had to stop it.
-How did you know that?
-I saw it.
-You saw it?
You couldn't have seen it from here.
Did he say why
he'd done all these things?
He said...
...that he wanted people to respect
and love me the way he did.
Why are you monitoring Viktoria's house?
-We're not doing that, it's all Oliver.
-Yes, but why?
He had a...twisted relationship
with his sister.
-Incestuous?
-No...
He'd watch her, and he'd film her...
but it wasn't mutual.
So Viktoria didn't know
her house was being monitored?
-But you knew?
-I found out a few days ago.
Oliver had been down here a lot,
and was acting weird.
How do you feel about Viktoria?
-Huh?
-I like her.
Both as my sister-in-law and as my boss.
She had nothing to do with this.
It was all Oliver...
Viktoria says Oliver confessed to some
crimes before he died. You heard him?
Our stock shot up almost seven points.
How do you think you got
that EU summit job?
-Boris died.
-Exactly.
I've always been there for you.
All these years.
The side effects of the intolerance drug
could have ruined us.
I dealt with that, too.
What do you mean?
I want everyone to respect you
the way I respect you.
The way I love you, Viktoria.
My finale will make you immortal.
You're going to save Europe.
-So...
-We're not done yet.
The finale is in motion
and "will make Viktoria immortal."
-And "she'll save Europe."
-The EU summit.
It's perfect.
The impact couldn't be greater.
Oliver didn't care about that. It was
all done for Viktoria and Medisonus.
-They're not mutually exclusive.
-How would an attack benefit Viktoria?
-Plus, she'll be there.
-Only briefly.
Oliver talked about Europe.
The EU summit is this week.
-There may very well be a connection.
-We proceed as if there is one.
-Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
-Martin Rohde.
-You're the one who's been calling.
-Yes.
FRIM has pulled Peter Thaulov, you ask
about my speaker... What's going on?
You recognize this man?
No, I...
You haven't seen him
in preparations for the summit?
-Might he do something at the summit?
-No. He's dead.
He may have planned something.
You need to beef up security.
-Who is he?
-Viktoria Nordgren's brother, Oliver.
Get this picture out
to anyone you work with.
We'll go over all your buildings again.
Check if anyone involved has been
a client of Copenhagen IT Consulting.
-Why?
-The attack may be computer-triggered.
Copenhagen IT Consulting?
They were involved
in an attack on a chemical plant.
-I'll make sure this gets out.
-Thank you.
I found chats with Julian on Oliver's
computer. Oliver was "Mother Of Three."
-We know that.
-Now we're positive.
Search Julian Madsen's computers again
for anything on the EU summit.
No, John's going home
to get some sleep - everyone is.
Another unit will go through
the material overnight.
-They know what they're looking for?
-I can tell them.
-I want to stay.
-You heard me!
-Hi.
-Where are you?
-Going to a friend's place.
-Your stuff's gone.
-Yes. I moved out.
-So you chose the living-apart option?
No, I chose to move out.
But we'll still see each other,
and do stuff, and have sex?
I don't think so. That didn't work.
-What's not working?
-Us. You and me.
You can have your own room, too.
-It's not about having our own rooms.
-Then what's it about?
What did I do wrong?
What's not working?
Obviously, you didn't want me around.
I do, just not everywhere, all the time.
If I'm with someone, I kind of need to
feel I can be everywhere all the time.
So we're not together anymore?
No, we're not together anymore.
Hey... I need to get some sleep.
I think I'm coming down with something.
Anything I can do for you?
I just need to get some sleep.
You want me to get you something?
No, thank you.
-Sleep tight.
-You too, honey.
What part of "get some sleep"
didn't you get?
Nothing, but I didn't want to sleep.
-We're releasing Thaulov.
-Why?
There wasn't enough to detain him.
He could still be Mikkel Höst.
He had alibis for all the times
the access card was used.
-It all points to Oliver.
-He did have palytoxin at home.
Yes, and he planted the access card
at Peter Thaulov's.
-How did he know we were looking for it?
-Gertrud knew. Maybe she mentioned it.
We'll have to ask her.
Jakob's moved out.
-What? Why?
-We're not together anymore.
I'm so sorry. How do you feel?
It's good to have the place to myself.
It's sad I failed as a girlfriend.
Right, that's understandable.
I put a lot of time into it.
More results would have been nice.
Julian and Ramon were both found in lye,
so we weren't meant to find them - why?
Oliver was methodical and organized.
He put them there to hide something.
-Did we have an appointment today?
-No.
So what are you doing here?
-You're going to help me find something.
-Oh, I am?
You're going to re-examine
Julian and Ramon.
What am I looking for?
Whatever they didn't want us to find,
since they were in lye.
-Morning. Thank you.
-You're welcome.
In here.
-Here's your change of clothes.
-Thank you.
I feel bad I didn't tell you
about the cameras.
It's all right.
Good thing they were there.
Or we wouldn't have proof of anything.
They actually thought it was you?
Yes, it would appear so.
I should have known...
...that everything wasn't right.
Yeah, I guess we both should have.
I don't think I've ever said
"thank you" to him or...
...complimented him or anything.
That's no reason
to go around killing people.
Hey... Won't you sit down for a bit?
No. I'm busy, so...
Come on, sit down.
Come here.
Hey. What you did,
or was forced to... Hey!
-Martin.
-Yes?
Good news and bad news. There's nothing
in Madsen's computers on the EU summit.
-What's the good news?
-I looked at Oliver's cell.
He received this text
a few hours before he died.
Pictamatic was the last site
he visited on his computer.
He never logged out
and only followed one user: Rekna125.
This image was posted yesterday.
And this one about three hours ago.
Can you find out
where that canister goes?
-And trace the phone that sent it.
-I'm on it.
Hey. Where have you been?
-The medical examiner.
-What the hell for?
Martin! I found the guy
that posted those pics.
Fabian Widman, 32 years old.
Lives in Copenhagen.
He's an aircraft technician at Kastrup.
-For fuck's sake!
-What pics...?
Let's go! The finale is on.
We're there in two minutes.
-The airport police detained Widman.
-Good.
If this canister does contain
an airborne contagion
and is on a plane due to land
in, say, Schiphol in Amsterdam,
it could theoretically spread
all over Europe within 24 hours.
Factor in people with connecting flights
infecting even more passengers...
-Then the scope widens.
-Yes. It'd spread globally.
This way, he's up here.
One or more flights may have
a biological weapon on board.
-Has it taken off?
-We don't know.
We're figuring out what flights
Fabian has had access to since midnight.
This is your captain.
We can't find a fault,
but a loss of cabin pressure
has been detected
so we ask all passengers
to put on your oxygen masks.
We will soon begin our descent
into Frankfurt, so please remain calm,
and follow the instructions
of the cabin crew. Thank you.
What's the flight
and what's in the canister?
-What's the flight?
-You know the emissions of air travel?
One roundtrip to Thailand
is like a year of driving.
What's the flight
and what's in the canister?
You sent a pic to Oliver Nordgren.
Do you know who he is?
You're an environmentalist? He doesn't
give a shit about you or about nature.
He's killed a bunch of you.
He doesn't give a fuck about nature!
He used you people. He used you!
He doesn't give a fuck about nature,
do you get that?
So what's the flight
and what's in the canister?
There is no sign of cabin pressure loss
anymore. You may take off your masks.
We apologize for this incident
and wish you a good day ahead.
Are you ready for that?
Oliver Nordgren is dead.
All the murders that are about to happen
will be on you. Are you ready for that?
Are you ready to go to jail for life?
To kill all those people?
-It's too late.
-What's too late?
-I connected it to the oxygen system.
Flight 443 to Frankfurt
had a loss of cabin pressure.
-Masks are on?
-Yes. They'll land now.
Then they're all infected.
What was in the canister?
-I don't know!
-Nobody gets off. Quarantine everyone.
The Kastrup flight was quarantined
in Frankfurt immediately upon landing.
All passengers,
22 of whom are Swedish,
are infected with the same
aggressive pneumonic plague
found on the ship
that ran aground some weeks ago.
Passengers have been quarantined.
Thanks to speedy antibiotic treatment
all passengers are expected to live.
What about the motive?
This attack has also been linked
to Oliver Nordgren.
The motive would be to strengthen
Medisonus' position on the market.
Was he acting alone?
Unconfirmed sources say a Copenhagen
IT firm delivered the plane's software.
-They are thought to be involved.
-Thanks, Fredrik...
-Does that mean we're done?
-Oliver confessed the whole thing.
There's a proven connection between him
and Julian Madsen. So yeah, we're done.
-Are we sure he was alone?
-Everything would suggest that.
I've got beers and sandwiches coming.
Lillian is on her way here.
I think I'll go home to Mette,
but thank you guys.
I'm going home, too.
Thank you, good teamwork.
-Thanks, I've learned a lot.
-OK.
-Great working with you.
-It was great working with you, too.
-You're good for me.
-Good.
-Don't let a year go by this time.
-No.
Saga...
I know what you and your sister
were subjected to as kids.
I Know your mother had Munchausen.
-How do you know?
-I read the report on your sister.
I read the report
on your sister's death.
-Saga...
-Don't!
Saga.
Saga, sometimes it's good
if other people know.
Saga!
-Hey.
-Hi...
Where are all the kids?
The big ones are with friends.
The little ones are with Mother.
OK.
That thing with Saga,
her sister... The suicide.
I tried talking to Saga about it.
It went really badly.
When Nikolaj was in the hospital...
It really felt as though we could
find our way back to each other.
The other night when we had sex...
I woke up, and I just
couldn't stay in bed.
I had to get up and leave.
I can't just pick up where we left off.
And keep going.
I just can't.
What are you saying?
I don't love you anymore.
I want you to move out.
-You came, after all.
-Your night shift guys were sloppy.
That, or you failed to tell them
what to look for.
These are the times
Mikkel Höst used his access card.
This is our emergency call
from when Laura Möllberg was shot.
Mikkel Höst used his card
five minutes before we called.
We know Oliver shot Laura Möllberg,
so he couldn't have been at Medisonus.
We're not done. There must be
at least another person involved.
Subtitles: Mario Bernengo
TC:subtitling
Edited by thedude95