-They claim it and leave a symbol.
-A pathos-driven eco-terrorism?
Negative human impact
on the environment - hence the symbol.
-You think there are more?
-These groups tend to work in cells.
One day you just felt so great
you decided to see your son's murderer?
I think you're fighting
to keep the old Jens at bay.
Nikolaj woke up. He's got a fever.
-I don't know what they'd do without me.
-Get another nanny.
Someone logged in
with the handle "Stressed Out Dad"...
...and chatted with someone
called "Mother Of Three."
-I didn't know it was part of the plan.
-Heard what they thought?
-She was gassed.
-She was my sister. Mathilde.
-So who was it?
-I don't know. Yet.
I'm meeting someone tonight.
Film it, you get another 5,000 kroner.
-Can you trace "Mother Of Three"?
-Not yet.
They discussed a "birthday party”
and a "graduation." There are more.
EPISODE 5
-You're late.
-Yes.
Hello... Hi.
Are you OK about last night?
-Totally. And you?
-Yeah.
Laura Möllberg is out of surgery.
Doctors say she'll live.
-Can we interrogate her?
-Yes. Later today.
No news about Julian Madsen.
Anything else?
Contents of the SD card
in Laura's camera are coming up.
The man who was hit at Katarina's place.
Copenhagen Police say
he never reported it to them.
Issue a description and a BOLO.
Progress on Madsen's computer
and Mother Of Three?
No, but the chat suggests Julian
was the group's only point of contact.
No one person has the whole picture.
A precaution.
Madsen wants to avenge his sister.
Uses Laura as collateral.
But Mother Of Three must have known
he was killing Julian's sister.
Doesn't seem like it.
Laura was shot, Madsen wasn't.
Why, and where is he?
Techs say they found a tranquilizer dart
in the vicinity of Laura's car.
-So he wanted him alive?
-That's a reasonable assumption.
Stop. Rewind.
Frame by frame.
-Stop. Can you do anything about that?
-Doubtful. The resolution is pretty bad.
-Try anyway.
-What about the blinking car?
I've got make and color,
but not the plates.
Do your best to get it.
Whoever it is
can't get to Julian that quickly.
-Two perps?
-Or one, remotely operating the blinker.
-To deflect attention.
-Is that possible?
It's actually pretty easy.
The shooter,
if he wasn't wearing a mask...
His position is dead ahead of Laura.
She must have seen him.
How do you know Viktoria Nordgren?
She's the keynote speaker
at the summit. Why?
She's sent you an email
where she OK's the pics.
-You're reading my emails?
-Are they secret?
No, but they're for me.
-Did you make an appointment?
-For what?
The clinic. Your birthday present.
I'm not doing it.
-Why not?
-Why should 1?
Will you sleep with me then?
If I've got bigger tits?
What do you mean? We have sex.
Do we? When's the last time we did?
-You're being silly.
-For wanting my man to take me?
Even if I'm not a D cup?
Some men find me attractive
just the way I am.
-Who?
-I don't know!
At work... Or when I go into town,
I can feel their eyes on me.
Any of them like white wine?
Hey... How's she doing?
-Why, what did you hear?
-Nothing. Just that she woke up.
Yes, she's incredibly lucky.
One went through her shoulder,
one grazed her breast, one her head.
-She'll make a full recovery.
-That's great.
-Did she say who shot her?
-No. She recalls nothing.
The last thing she remembers
is Julian and her leaving our house.
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
Martin Rohde, Copenhagen Police.
-Did you see who shot you?
-No.
-You were at Julian's office.
-Yes.
- I tipped him off.
-We know. That's aiding and abetting.
-Would you have arrested him otherwise?
-Maybe.
Do you know who Julian was meeting?
-His sister's murderer.
-Did he mention any names?
He didn't know him.
They made plans to meet online.
You're sure he didn't say
who you were meeting?
-Positive.
-Your dad says you recall nothing.
You were filming from a roof.
You were at Malmö Stadium.
Yes, I recall bringing a camera.
You filmed whoever Julian was meeting.
Then you were shot in your car.
Sorry, I don't recall.
We'd like for you to come with us.
Come on, Laura.
You don't recall being here?
You don't recognize it?
-You were up on that roof.
-I don't remember.
Over there was a car
with the blinkers on.
A white car.
Julian Madsen fell
to the ground right here.
Then a man came towards him.
Get in the car.
Other side.
The shooter was dead ahead of you.
You must have seen him.
What does he look like?
You've gotten down from the roof.
He's chasing you.
You get in the car.
Why don't you drive away?
- I didn't have my keys.
-What do you do?
You try to hide? Get out of the car?
Call someone?
-I grab...my phone.
-But there's no time to call anyone?
I don't know.
Look at me. Your shooter
was standing dead ahead of you.
Laura, look at me.
You must have seen him.
What did he look like?
You're getting shot.
Where does the first bullet hit you?
-Saga...
-You looked up when you got shot.
Laura, what did he look like?
You want to recall this.
-Laura!
-Saga...
What does he look like?
Laura? Laura?
Axel Möllberg? Hi, I'm Beate.
I was the one who...
-I was Laura's teacher.
-Right, sure. Hi.
I saw in the paper Laura had come to.
How is she?
As good as she can be.
She's not here right now.
The police wanted her for something.
-OK.
-Hey...
You know it wasn't Laura who spoke
to the principal? It was me.
-No, I did not know that.
-Well, I did.
I just felt it was wrong.
Not the fact that you were dating,
I don't have a problem with that.
-It's just that you were her teacher.
-Right...
-But I'm not anymore.
-No, right...
Well, say hi for me.
Tell her I was here.
But hey, wait in her room.
It's on the second floor, room 8.
Right. Thank you.
-I want to write a book.
-Everyone does.
I mean it, I'm serious.
Yes, so am I.
And what would your book be about?
It'll be about me.
You know I love you dearly, but you
specifically are better in person.
I think it could be a really great book.
I've known a lot of women in my day.
Interesting women. Famous women.
How famous?
You're lying. She just got married!
-It was a while back.
-Isn't she a lesbian?
-Not that night, I assure you.
-She just had a kid.
I had no part in that,
I can promise you that.
How long have you been doing this?
Just over twenty-five years.
You were but a child!
How did you get started?
What do you say? How about that book?
-You're changing the subject.
-Yes, I am.
I'll see what I can do.
Where's your security?
-You caused her to faint?
-She lost consciousness briefly, yes.
I trusted you, but you two
won't get near her again.
Yes. If the investigation
calls for it, we will.
-What's happened here?
-A fatality in Laura's room.
We called the police.
They told us not to go in there.
-Who is she?
-Beate Frelle.
Identical symptoms.
Is there anything edible in here?
No, there's no food here.
Claudio may be writing a book for me.
OK...
It'll be rather revealing.
Not to worry, I'll leave you out of it.
No need. Nothing happened.
-You didn't call him?
-Yes.
-But you didn't fuck?
-No.
-Why not?
-I couldn't...
-You sissy.
-It just felt wrong.
I don't want to be like Alexander.
I think he's cheating on me.
Are we talking about the same guy?
Alexander, your husband? The monk?
He's out late more.
Going on more business trips.
He got home really late last night.
He said his flight was delayed.
-It wasn't?
-No, I checked with Kastrup.
And it doesn't stop him
from getting jealous.
He doesn't want you,
but damn if anyone else touches you.
-You know what I think you should do.
-No!
Yes! Call Claudio. Give him
something to be jealous about.
It'll be good for you, Caroline.
Why was the room not guarded?
Where was the uniform on duty?
He took a break
when you came to get Laura.
How did the perp know
that Laura had come to?
It was leaked to the press,
unfortunately.
OK. Thank you.
The hospital has no CCTV on that floor.
Just two cams on the main entrance.
-Where's the footage?
-On its way.
But it's not hard to get in elsewhere,
and the rooms aren't locked.
We need to get organized.
Rasmus! You're in charge
of Julian Madsen. Focus on him.
Pernille, you take the hospital. Get John
to help you with the CCTV footage.
Then you report back to Saga and Martin.
-Ten thousand...
-What's that?
I was supposed to get 10,000 kroner
for helping Julian.
And now Beate is dead.
For ten thousand...
If I hadn't helped Julian or gone
to the police, she'd be alive now.
We don't always know the consequences
of all the choices we make.
If she hadn't come here,
she wouldn't be dead.
Honey... It was chance.
There were so many things factoring in.
Laura Möllberg. 18 years old.
Top of her class.
Popular. Conscientious.
She sailed, rode horses...
Worked part-time at an IT firm.
Had a brilliant future ahead of her.
Until she was shot, three times.
There was a time, you'd have worked
24/7 to nail the guy who did it.
-How's the food in here?
-What do you mean?
Anything you miss?
Anything you want me to bring you?
- I go past the Indian place every day.
-No, thanks.
This here is a copy of the case file
Saga and I are working on.
I'm not a cop anymore.
-You don't say?
-That's right.
So don't read it.
Let go of me!
Let me go! Let me go!
This came a few minutes ago.
-Ever seen her before?
-No.
-Is this a new group?
-It's a cell.
She's involved with animal testing...
...and her name is Rakel.
They want a law passed
in 12 hours. That's impossible.
They want to kill her.
Got her. Rakel Richardsson is her name.
University Hospital research department.
-Divorced. Daughter.
-Is it her or her daughter's birthday?
-Their next act was the "birthday."
-March and June.
Got an address?
-How old is her daughter?
-She's fourteen.
Let's hope
she's with her father this week.
Saga!
Nothing.
Nothing in the basement, either?
Copenhagen Police, Martin Rohde.
We'll turn you loose.
She saw nothing.
Animal masks and dark clothing.
-Techs are at the house now.
-Did they find a golden toad?
Not yet, but they're there.
They didn't wear them.
Saga, Martin... Come here for a sec.
I've filtered the audio from this video.
-That was fast.
-It wasn't very hard.
This is the background noise, amped up.
-Geese?
-They're everywhere. The other thing?
-It's a wind farm.
-How do you know?
There's one right by
my parents' summer cabin.
Sounds exactly like that.
Techs are done
with Rakel Richardsson's house.
They found a snuff box in the backyard
with finger prints on it.
-Carl Sjöberg.
-Known animal rights activist.
He's got priors. Assaulting an officer,
rioting, vandalism, et cetera.
Lives in a collective in Kirseberg.
There are 324 wind farms in Skåne,
over 1,000 on Sealand.
I put them on a map.
I'll look for nearby houses.
-Got anything?
-Not yet.
So why are you telling us?
Um, because I'm working on it.
So you're telling us you're working?
We're going to the collective
in Kirseberg.
The collective was empty.
Camilla Gunnarsson, Rebecca Ståhl,
and Thomas Dahlberg share that address.
All but Thomas are known activists.
Camilla Gunnarsson. She and her
brother own a summer cabin together.
-Where?
-Outside something called Gissholm.
Got an address?
Where's that map of the wind farms?
On the server.
Those are the wind farms...
...and the summer cabin is right here.
Police!
-Clear?
-All clear!
-Let me out!
-Soon. Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
The people who did this,
did they say where they were going?
-Anything that tells us where they went?
-There were four...
-We know. Where were they going?
-I don't know!
-Focus! It's important.
-Where is my daughter?
If we're going to get them,
you must try to focus.
-Saga! They found Julian Madsen.
-Where?
Your daughter is with her father.
How do we know it's Julian Madsen?
He had a metal plate in his leg
after a skiing accident.
-What's this site?
-Hazardous waste disposal.
-They process it.
-And dump it in West Africa...
You don't know that.
Jesper Lauge is the facility supervisor.
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
What's in these?
We're not really sure,
but it might be potassium hydroxide.
Lye? How come you're not sure?
It sat among other barrels of potassium
hydroxide from D&C chemical company.
But we've checked,
and they delivered 16 barrels yesterday.
But that one makes it 17.
-No signs of forced entry?
-No.
And we're working
around the clock right now.
We need a list of all your employees.
-You think it's one of ours?
-We can't rule it out.
Tape your interviews with the employees.
Then send them to us.
-Why dissolve him?
-So we don't find him?
But why? The others
were left for us to find.
Yeah...
We'll make a little detour
on the way back.
-Hello!
-Hi! It's you.
I'm going to check in on Nikolaj.
-So you're back?
-Yes.
I'm thirsty!
And we want to watch a movie.
No. That's Nikolaj's.
I'll get you another drink.
-Who are you?
-We've met. Don't you remember?
Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
I work with Martin.
-You want to see my play tomorrow?
-No, I don't.
-She doesn't like kids.
-Why not?
I do like kids. I just don't like them
automatically just because they're kids.
-Do you like me?
-I don't know.
I don't know you well enough
to determine that.
Will you be
at the press conference tonight?
-Sure, if you really want me there.
-I do. Really.
I'll see you later.
-Got a minute, Martin?
-Now?
Yes, now.
Sit.
You gave Jens the case file?
-Parts of it.
-He's serving a life sentence!
-I'll make sure he knows what he did.
-He knows.
In here! But not in here.
I'll make sure he feels
what he did, in here.
His plan was to die, so he wouldn't have
to face the consequences of what he did.
So now he's struggling. He's built
a protective wall around himself.
I'm going to tear that wall down.
Let's say you manage
to do that... Then what?
Then I win. Then I get to him,
the way he's gotten to me.
That's a big risk for something
that may never happen.
I gotta believe I have a shot.
Well, you can't give him access
to an ongoing investigation.
I needed a way in!
Just make sure to get it back.
-What did Lillian want?
-Nothing important.
-You're off?
-Yes. See you tomorrow.
-Can I come with you?
-Of course you can.
Bye.
So you'll let me back in that car?
Yeah.
Hi. I'm going to take
a quick shower. I'm off again.
-Where are you going?
-Work dinner.
-You could have said something.
-Sorry. It was decided today.
Saga, Techs say Julian's barrel had
a lot more prints on it than the others.
-You know whose?
-Mostly this guy's... Sammy Nyrop.
I'm going through
his interview tape right now.
-You're off?
-Yes.
I thought you'd be right back.
I mean, no "bye."
-Not until tomorrow.
-OK. Bye. Catch you tomorrow.
Why would you catch me?
You mean we'll see each other.
-Yep. That's what I meant.
-Bye!
Bye...
Sammy, Sammy...
You're lying through your teeth.
-Hey!
-Hi, it's me.
-You on your way home?
-No, I'm not coming home.
-You need to work?
-No.
So...what are you doing?
-I've checked into a hotel.
-What? Here, in Malmö?
-Yes.
-Why?
I need to be alone.
I haven't been alone in over a week.
You could've said so. I could've met up
with someone or gone to the movies.
-But you'd be home after.
-Well, yeah, I live here.
Then I wouldn't be alone.
OK... So how long
are you going to stay at the hotel?
I don't know. A night or two.
I'm in no way questioning
our relationship.
I just need some quality alone time.
Maybe you won't stop reading
those relationship books
but you gotta stop sounding like them.
-But it's true.
-Good to know.
OK, so...have some quality alone time,
and I guess we'll talk tomorrow.
Yes.
I didn't know
there was a body in the barrel.
I was told to pick it up
and put it with the others.
-So this isn't the first time?
-No, the fourth.
-What exactly do you do?
-I get a text with a pick-up location.
I let it disappear with the other waste.
It never occurred to you
something illegal might be going on?
No, maybe someone dodging fees
or environmental inspections.
Are you stupid?
Environmental inspections? Fees?
OK, I knew it was probably
something illegal.
But I never checked the barrels.
I figured they were smuggling something.
-How did they first approach you?
-I got a letter.
-You still have it?
-No.
What did it say?
At first I thought it was
one of those quick-money scams.
-But...it was personal.
-Personal, how?
They knew where I worked, what I did.
And that I have some...problems.
What problems?
I gamble occasionally.
He gets texts with pick-up points
and where to collect his money.
-John is trying to trace the texts.
-What do we do with him?
It's unlikely whoever hires him
monitors him constantly.
-So he doesn't know we have him?
-Probably not.
We'll let him go and put a tail on him.
CAROLINE:
HI. CAN WE MEET TONIGHT?
I'D LOVE TO. WHERE AND WHEN?
CAROLINE:
THE PAVILION AT THE PARK AT 9 P.M.
You acted outside your jurisdiction
in official police business
and brought a Danish national to Sweden
without clearing it with Danish police.
-So I'm reporting you to IA.
-You're kidding.
No.
Maybe you should thank me instead.
I brought this investigation
closer to resolution.
That depends on whether
he gets in touch with him again.
What the hell goes on in your head?
Get real! I still brought him here.
That's got to account for something.
Yes. I'm not critical of the results,
I'm critical of your methods.
Right off the bat, it's plain to see
something's seriously wrong with you.
But this... How the fuck
are you allowed to be on the force?
-I'm an excellent detective.
-Right...
Over-analytical robots devoid of any
emotions are just what the force needs.
The fuck...
You agree with Rasmus?
No. You know I don't. I just
don't think you should report him.
-But he broke the rules.
-But he did good.
Yes, but he didn't do it right.
He can't talk to you like that,
that was extremely mean.
He was way out of line
and owes you an apology.
-He's not the first.
-To be that mean to you?
To think I'm incapable of getting hurt.
Saga, it's ready for you. Saga!
He chose his sites carefully.
Four barrels, four different sites.
-I wonder what was in the other three.
-Has Lillian sent out Techs?
He probably doesn't know we found
Julian. We should lay off the site.
-Where are you going?
-To see my daughter's play.
-What's the play?
-Red Riding Hood.
-You're going home, too?
-No, I'm staying at a hotel.
-You and Jakob had a fight?
-No, I just need to be alone.
-So you check into a hotel?
-Yes.
-Karin and I are getting a divorce.
-Why is that?
It's just not working anymore.
-Did you cheat on her?
-No!
Men are more likely than women
to leave for someone else.
-Did Karin cheat on you?
-No, I don't think so.
This was nice, but I assume
you didn't just invite me to dinner.
Well, no...
I'd like for you to do
my sister Viktoria's memoirs.
This is my second proposal
for an autobiography in two days.
I don't know who the other person is
but I'm certain my sister's
will garner more attention.
Another kind of attention, at any rate.
How is she?
The doctors give her six months.
Knowing her, that means
at least another 18 months.
She's a remarkable woman.
She's the keynote speaker
at the EU summit.
She's on the Forbes list
of female business leaders.
I think there's a global market.
Oliver, you don't need to sell me on it.
We'll be honored to publish it.
I'm thinking more in practical terms.
Is she up to writing it?
Does she want to co-author it
with someone, or what?
I was thinking you'd write it.
I haven't written anything
in a long time.
But your writing was good.
And we trust you.
Excuse me, I need to reply to this.
ABOUT TO SEE YOUR SISTER
GOOD FOR HER!
That was the other autobiography writer.
And what does he or she do?
He is in the...entertainment business.
And his name is Claudio.
Cheers to that.
-Mom, what do I do with these flowers?
-Leave them, I'll take care of them.
You were the best Red Riding Hood ever.
-Thank you.
-No, thank you. Good night, then.
And make sure to hug
your brothers and sisters for me.
-Good night.
-Good night. Night, kiddo.
It's good you came.
It means a lot to Johanne.
It's late, and it's a school night.
I'd better tuck them in.
But thanks for the ride.
I'm doing better. Something good
will come of my meetings with Jens.
Listen, I'd rather not hear about Jens.
OK. But I'm doing much better.
Mette! Come to the bathroom!
-What's wrong?
-He needed to pee before bed.
Oh, but honey...!
There's blood in his pee.
He's burning up.
Honey, it's going to be all right.
-Hey... How's it going?
-Good. I'm staying another night.
OK. Mom's coming tomorrow.
It'd be nice if you were here.
Yes, I will be.
Have you told her about me?
-Of course.
-What did you tell her?
That you're amazing in every way.
Then her expectations
will likely be too high.
I doubt it - it's true. Another session
starts in 14 seconds. I've gotta go.
-OK.
-OK. Good night.
Subtitles: Mario Bernengo
TC:subtitling
Edited by thedude95