Five people were chained below deck.
They were likely kidnapped.
-I can get someone else to help you.
-Why not Martin?
I don't know how he'll respond
to seeing you again.
Goddamn, it's been ages!
I don't live with Mette anymore.
But we had twins, did you know?
Oh? I'm living with a guy
named Jakob Sandberg.
I want to get good at this.
At having a relationship.
I know who were on that ship.
A bouncer saw them leave at 03.45.
-There's a cam there.
-I'll put John on it.
-There was a fox...
-Flashing lights.
You'd think they were
abducted by aliens.
-Did that ship run aground?
-I don't know.
We will get a 12,
with me doing all the work.
-Hi...
-I'm at the stables with Tina.
Do you know what happened to Maria?
-I keep seeing him.
-Jens, who killed your son?
Everywhere. He's in here.
I'm lying to myself and others.
But inside, nothing's happening.
What the hell are you doing?
Put it out!
I want to see Jens in prison.
-Axel Möllberg. I've got some footage.
-You saw where it headed after?
Saga, you need to come with me now.
Two more have died - from pneumonic
plague. We're to be quarantined.
I've been with Mette and the kids.
Someone's trying to cause an outbreak
of pneumonic plague.
EPISODE 2
Three people have died at Skåne
University Hospital in Malmö.
Another two are in critical condition.
With us now is Filippa Belinder,
from the Institute for Disease Control.
-What should one do if infected?
-See a doctor.
Especially if you display the symptoms
high fever, racing pulse, cough...
...breathing difficulties, and chest
pains. But this disease is treatable.
Did she say that? Anna-Dea said that?
In that case I think you should do that.
No? Yes, I'll be by soon. Bye.
Third time you've talked to them today.
Just to make sure they're fine.
Can you blame me?
It spreads primarily through coughing,
and you're not coughing.
-Now you're a virus expert?
-It's not a virus, but a bacterium.
Think out loud, Saga.
Someone kidnaps five people,
gives them the plague...
...and puts them on a ship
that runs aground.
No one's claimed it after two days.
Both of your test results
came back negative.
-And negative is a good thing here?
-That's correct.
I need to talk
to the Faxborg kids again.
As you may know,
we lost another one this morning.
But there are two left, right?
Their condition is critical.
The antibiotics aren't working.
-So maybe once they're stable.
-No, not maybe. You'll call.
-You ready?
-Yes.
-Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
-Pernille Lindegaard, Copenhagen Police.
We're here to assist
with the five kids from the boat.
It's a ship. And three of them are dead.
-Hi.
-Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
Rasmus Larsson.
I've looked into these plague bacteria.
Basically all hospitals and research
centers in the region stockpile them.
These bacteria are impossible to trace.
-Hi, I'm Martin. Welcome on board.
-Thank you.
-Hi. Rasmus Larsson.
-Hi.
-You know her?
-I've seen you before, but no.
-No. Great to work with you.
-Yeah, likewise.
-Want to get some coffee?
-Sure.
-Rasmus!
-Come on, Rasmus.
-John!
-Yes?
-Heard from Helsingør?
-I haven't received the footage.
-Why not?
-I don't know. I'm on them.
But they're taking their time.
-Saga, they found the life raft.
-Where?
A farmer north of Lomma saw them
come ashore two days ago.
He called the police yesterday,
but no one came out.
Check the coastline. Lomma.
-Pernilla?
-Pernille. With an E.
Pernille? Right. Go to Helsingør
to get some footage from them.
-I could do it.
-No.
They found the life raft.
It's not personal.
She doesn't know my name either.
-Where are you going?
-With you.
No. Try to connect places that stockpile
plague bacteria to any of those kids.
OK...
-There were three of them.
-Men or women?
I don't know. They had
these thick jumpsuits and hats on.
-Both men and women, I think.
-You think or you know?
I know they ran up to a car
that was waiting up there.
-What make and color?
-I don't know cars. But it was red.
-Big or small?
-Pretty small. And red.
Yes, you mentioned that.
Did you see the number plates?
-Someone was waiting in the car?
-Yes.
-Man or woman?
-I don't know.
The only thing I recall
is that it was red.
Saying it over and over
doesn't make it more helpful.
-How did it go?
-We found it. Techs are looking at it.
Three people
left Faxborg in a life raft.
A fourth person was waiting
in a red vehicle...there.
-A red vehicle? Is that all you got?
-Yes. That it's red. And small.
Saga, these kids can't be connected to
places that stockpile plague bacteria.
No, I didn't think so.
Saga, Martin, come look at this.
This video was posted online
and got over 4,000 hits in an hour.
The clip is called "Friends of Faxborg."
What the hell is it?
Angola had an outbreak of pneumonic
plague in May. WHO says 319 people died.
Three in the life raft, one in the car.
"The world is bigger than us."
They said something
about a fox in the hospital.
So they're claiming responsibility.
Their message is online, too.
It doesn't prove they did it.
Zoom in. The pin on the jacket.
This was found on Maria Holst.
This group has the knowhow and resources
to steal a ship, kidnap five people...
...retrieve and handle plague bacteria.
They claim it, leave a symbol.
You know why they leave a symbol.
So people know it's them next time.
Hello!
Hi...
-Hello!
-Hi, Frida!
Frida!
Does it hurt?
No.
Nice try. Here you go.
Why did you do it, Linus?
-Was it for money? Why?
-No!
I just wanted to show those guys.
So they'd let me in for real.
-Point them out.
-Come on.
Point them out.
Hey! You guys!
I'm Niklas, Linus' brother.
-You hang out together, yeah?
-Sometimes.
Anyway, he's doing fine.
He's out and he'll make a full recovery.
You're Albin, right?
It wasn't my idea. He did it himself.
None of us forced him.
You didn't exactly try
to stop him, either.
Nice meeting you guys. Take care.
The rat definitely looks like a man.
The pig is probably also a man.
-This frog has appeared again.
-More infected?
No, a woman has died
from a poisoned apple.
Was her name Snow White?
We should talk to her step mom.
-Where did she die?
-At work.
They had fruit delivered to the office.
All baskets are being recalled.
-We've issued a warning.
-Saga! I'm coming with.
-Why?
-It'd be good to get out there.
So why don't you go for a walk?
Then try to trace those animal masks.
-We're just devastated.
-Do you stock the fruit here?
No, we get daily deliveries
from different delivery companies.
I've printed out a list of them.
I've also got a list
of all our employees.
-I figured you'd want one.
-Yes.
There are seven of us,
eight including me.
They start at six
and work until about nine or ten.
-Once you pack the baskets, then what?
-They go here.
-No surveillance cameras?
-No.
The trailers are lined up,
and the truckers pick them up.
-That's always open?
-Yes, for the most part.
-Have you seen this thing before?
-No.
-Positive?
-No, I don't...
-We're going to take a look around.
-Go ahead.
Saga! He came in this way.
Make sure the kids stay away
from fruit for the time being.
Great. Tell them I said hi
and hug them for me.
Bye.
-Who was that?
-Jakob.
-You didn't want to talk to him?
-No, I'm working.
-What does he do?
-I don't know.
After months of dating
you don't know what he does?
Should I?
If he doesn't want to say,
and you're not interested...
It's fantasy...comics or something.
I'm not really interested.
Does that make me a bad girlfriend?
-Does he ask you about your work?
-Yes.
It's a third of one's life.
If you ask him about his work,
you seem to take interest in him.
-Did you get the footage?
-Yes.
Our Helsingør colleagues are many things
but organized is not one.
-When did they leave the club?
-At 3.45 a.m.
Right...
This is where they leave.
Pause it!
Zoom in. The guy
on the right was not on the ship.
Where are the fruit company staff pics?
Mads Nielsen.
It's him. This is his address and info.
Martin Rohde, Copenhagen Police.
-Is Mads Nielsen here?
-Who?
Please step outside
so we can get into the apartment.
-You're with the police, too?
-Yes.
Can you do something about my neighbor?
They're playing music 24/7, and loud!
I've told him off.
It doesn't do any good.
-They're not playing it right now.
-No...
You said they played it 24/7.
-He's not here.
-Too bad.
I could use a man around the house.
Don't laugh if it's not funny to you.
I acknowledge their attempts
at being amusing.
-It comes across as fake.
-So I'll practice.
-Or maybe don't do it.
-It's Pernille with his info.
No registered phone number.
He does have a record.
Petty drug charges
and assaulting officers at protests.
-Protests against what?
-Nuclear power. The G8 meeting.
Used to be in
a Copenhagen activist group.
-Got an address?
-Yep.
Up there.
Hey! It costs money to park there.
Hey! I'm talking to you!
-Martin Rohde.
-Saga Norén, Malmö County Police.
-Will you be at the EU summit?
-Yes. Want to see our plans?
-Yes, please.
-Another time. We're looking for Mads.
-Mads Nielsen.
-No idea where he is.
-We threw that idiot out.
-Oh? Why?
He didn't fit in.
-Why was that?
-We threw him out three years ago.
He wanted to go from activism
to terrorism. We did not.
-Know where to find him?
-I want no part of him.
-Know anyone who hangs out with him?
-Sorry.
-Have you seen this before?
-No.
-Look at it.
If you think of something
related to Mads, call me.
STILL HANG OUT WITH MAD MADS?
COPS ARE LOOKING FOR HIM /A
-It costs money to park here.
-Get away from the car.
I said, it costs money to park here.
-What don't you get?
-Go away.
It costs money.
You're parked on my turf!
-Get away from the car.
-It costs money to park here. Got it?
Get the fuck out of here!
Beat it, I said!
Get out of here!
Get the fuck out of here!
Fuck!
Get in the car.
-Just say it.
-What?
-It was fucking stupid!
-Yes, it was.
They could report you.
I'd be a witness.
Did you see Jens in him?
Only two people got a 12 this time.
So either my test was very hard,
or you didn't study hard enough.
There you go.
We're not going to move on
with so many people missing.
Instead we'll go through
the test thoroughly.
- I just need to step out for a bit.
-Sure. Let's begin...
Hi, honey. What's going on?
Did they close the school?
-No, why would they?
-Maybe because of that plague.
I need 1,100 kroner.
-For what?
-A pair of shoes.
-For 1,100 kroner?
-1,600 actually. I've got 400 kroner.
You've got your allowance and your pay
from the IT company. That's it.
-I got a ten on my math test.
-Great. You must be happy.
-Do I look happy?
-You demand too much of yourself.
If you get this upset over a grade,
how will you cope with real adversity?
-The idea is not to have any.
-That won't cut it. OK?
If you need a pick-me-up, you can
decide what we're having for dinner.
I don't want fucking dinner.
Pharmaceuticals are the big winners
with a near 8 percent increase...
...largely due to a surge in demand for
antibiotics to treat pneumonic plague.
-No, no.
-Economy is boring if you're broke.
Forget about those shoes.
Easy for you to say, it's your fault.
If you'd given me a 12,
I wouldn't be so down.
Should I grade you better
because we're sleeping together?
-Yes, that would have been nice.
-It's also dishonest.
How do you think you get ahead in life?
Wow, that's a new one.
-You can buy them for me.
-Why would I do that?
-I figure it's worth 1,500 kroner.
-What is?
You are my teacher after all.
That's not funny, Laura.
Good. Because I'm not joking.
Laura? What's going on?
-I'll pick them up tomorrow.
-Come on, Laura...
Laura!
-I'm going to bed.
-Good night, honey.
Be quiet! Be quiet, I said!
Remember me? Linus' brother?
When I was a kid, you know what
my parents and teachers told me?
When I didn't get to play
with the others?
"You can't force kids to play together,
to like each other."
Well, I believe you can.
Do we understand each other?
-You're late.
-Had to deal with something.
-Punctuality. Don't underestimate it.
-We've got bigger problems.
You're wanted by the police.
Astrid texted me, said the cops came.
-When was that?
-A while ago.
And you didn't say anything?
Maybe we should change locations.
What's up, Katarina?
-People are dying.
-Yes?
It was one thing to plan it,
another thing to carry it out.
Right, it's huge.
Then we feel differently about it.
-You have regrets?
-No.
But they died. That's the thing.
You're awfully quiet.
I like it. I like that it's growing.
-I'm here for the shoot, then I'm done.
-What?
I can't keep doing this.
I'm responsible for Linus.
I'm all he's got.
Nobody gets out, OK?
Finish those signs. I'll get the camera.
We've issued a warrant
for Mads Nielsen.
From the Copenhagen
Climate Change Conference in 2009.
-You see her?
-Astrid. Can we put surveillance on her?
That will drain a lot of resources.
What are we doing about the tail
on Marcus Stenberg?
Anything besides Faxborg tying him
to the contagion or the poisonings?
Well, then we drop him.
Mads Nielsen did a few months
for assaulting an officer.
Here's a file on him, the group,
and similar networks in the region.
-And you?
-The fruit companies were a dud.
About a hundred stores
carry those animal masks.
I couldn't find anything
on the frog amulet.
I'd say they made it themselves.
Would it kill you to say thanks?
No.
I gave you something, you took it.
A "thanks" would be nice.
Right. Thanks.
-I'm out of here.
-Bye.
-You've got a car?
-Yes.
-Can you give me a ride?
-Of course.
Bye.
The Institute for Disease Control
projects limited spread
but cautions the public
to remain vigilant of any symptoms.
-What are you doing?
-I'm reading.
I can see that. What are you reading?
"Transmetropolitan Lust for Life.”
-You like it?
-No, I don't like comic books.
-So why are you reading it?
-I'm taking an interest in your work.
-Your books told you to do that?
-No, Martin told me to.
My job isn't just reading comics.
There's a business side to it.
Yes.
But you couldn't care less
what I do at work?
No. But I could care about it.
Sure, or you could stop paying
attention to that guy, Martin.
-Are you annoyed with me now?
-A little bit.
It's me again. Listen, I'm sorry.
Please call me back and I'll explain.
I had a lousy day
and I took it out on you. I'm sorry.
Your math teacher called.
Laura, wait. Wait!
-Why are you doing this? For some shoes?
-It wasn't for the shoes.
So help me out, I don't get it...
No, and you'll never get it.
You're always so fucking content.
-Jesus, you scared the shit out of me.
-You're the pig.
-I saw your scar. You guys kill people.
-Linus, listen to me...
Fucking murderers.
You kill people!
Fucking murderers!
-Linus...
-Fucking murderers! You kill people!
-Murderer! I don't want to be alone.
-You won't be.
-You don't know!
-I will if they catch you.
-They won't.
-You don't know! Murderer!
-Listen to me, Linus!
I get them things through work.
I'm sort of part of the group, but I've
never killed anyone. You hear me?
You hear me? I'm not leaving you.
I promise.
The wife found them like this. I think
the dad tried to reach the phone.
Same symptoms
as the woman with the apple.
Different-colored liquids
in the glasses.
Is Martin coming?
-No.
-But he's all right?
Yes. I'm going to try to find
the receipt for this thing.
-Pulling night shifts now?
-I thought it'd be empty.
-I bet you did. What are you doing here?
-I can't really go home.
I thought I could crash here.
-Why can't you go home?
-Had a fight with Dad.
-And your partner?
-I don't want to see her right now.
Can I stay? Just for tonight?
-Sure, why the hell not?
-Thanks. You're the best.
-Hey, you know anyone looking for a job?
-Why?
-Lene is on sick leave.
-I can work the reception desk.
It's full time. You're in school.
-I'll see if I can find someone.
-Great.
Good night.
Good morning.
A father and two kids died last night.
Poisoned by tiger prawns.
This morning, we found a golden frog
by the frozen prawns in the supermarket.
We've issued a warning and cautioned
the whole food-supply chain...
...to look out for a golden frog.
Here's a preliminary report.
-Did you write this?
-Yes.
-You were at the crime scene last night?
-I was thinking about the symbol.
-The frog?
-It's a toad.
-Whatever, reptiles.
-They're amphibians, not reptiles.
-Saga...
-Yes?
-Just... keep going.
Yes. So, "the golden toad."
Could be found in Costa Rica until 1989.
Went extinct due to climate change
and pollution - human interference.
There's a pattern. The tiger prawn
industry destroys the mangroves.
In Sweden we've seen calls
for boycotting them.
The poisoned apples were South African.
Transports impact the environment.
It's all about the negative human impact
on the environment. Hence the symbol.
The plague was a way to point
to third-world injustices.
So that's what we're dealing with?
A pathos-driven eco-terrorism of sorts?
Yes. "The world is bigger than us."
Saga, Martin... There's been
another probable poisoning.
Why didn't you answer
my call last night?
I was busy.
-Going over that family's place?
-Yes.
Why didn't you call me?
I figured you needed to sleep.
Just because you learned to lie
doesn't mean you're any good at it.
I told you I like working with you again
because you treat me like you used to.
Yes, but you're not like you used to be.
No. That may be true.
But I don't want special treatment.
I thought you of all people
would understand that.
I'm sorry.
Boris Williams, age 54, a Lund University
professor of Environmental Economics.
Rib-eye.
-What are you looking for?
-Where he got the meat.
-How do you know it was the meat?
-Biggest environmental impact.
-Martin.
-Five more stores have called.
-They've all found amulets.
-It's spreading. Five more stores.
Two of them have CCTV. I've asked
them to send John the footage.
Mads Nielsen worked
for the fruit company.
Get lists of the store employees,
but focus on the newest ones.
-OK.
-Was one of the stores Ölanders Livs?
-No.
-Is Rasmus there?
-Yes.
-Tell him to go to Ölanders Livs.
Tell him to look for the toad
among imported meats.
-Then have them shut down.
-Shouldn't a uniformed cop do that?
-Yes. But he wanted to get out there.
-OK.
Yes, with the police?
-Saga?
-The entry code is 0315.
All clear.
No, turn that off.
It enhances the effects of the drugs.
They kept them here
before putting them on the ship.
Don't touch it, Saga.
Saga! They had the plague.
Come on, let's get out of here.
John? You know who tipped us off
to the harbor location?
I couldn't trace the call.
But check this out.
It's CCTV footage from the stores.
That girl.
At 1.45 p.m. she's in Malmö.
She enters...
Then, one hour later...
...she's in Copenhagen.
-Can you zoom in?
-Yes, but it won't be any clearer.
Print out
the sharpest image you can get.
Saga! It's a new clip.
Looks like you were right.
Yes.
What's up?
Why are we meeting here?
-The cops came to the harbor.
-How did they find us?
That's what we'd like to know.
What...? You think it was me?
Give me your phone.
I said, give me your phone.
-Mads...
-You shut up.
-OK. Tonight, as planned.
-They've already OK'd something?
-This is our own initiative.
-Wait, if the cops know who we are...
They knew about the harbor,
that's it. We're on for tonight.
OK.
-Where are you going?
-Fix dinner for Linus.
-We're all staying put.
-Come on!
-How old is this kid anyway?
-Thirteen.
At thirteen, I was taking care
of myself. Sit down.
Sit down.
OK.
This is the plan.
Could you help us?
Our car broke down.
Mads, what the fuck?
Cut it out, let's go!
Check it out.
What am I looking at?
That's five gallons of gas.
We just got hold of
five thousand gallons of gas.
Subtitles: Mario Bernengo
TC:subtitling
Edited by thedude95