(ENGINE REVVING)
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLASTS)
ReEncoded By Dr.XJ | PSA
www.PSArips.com
(CHEERING)
Hello, everybody. Hel-lo!
(WHISTLING)
-Hello!
-Thank you.
-Thank you, everybody.
-Hello!
Thank you, thank you,
thank you.
RICHARD:
Hello!
Thank you so much, everybody.
Thank you. Now...
Coming up
in this week's show:
A supercar
is dismantled for no reason.
A man with no shirt on.
And my whole tongue
is wrapped up in intestine.
My whole tongue
Those are the highlights.
-Those are the best bits.
-Yep.
They really are.
Anyway...
over here in the West,
we tend to think
that at £360,000
a Rolls Royce Phantom
is quite expensive.
But this week, The Grand Tour
is focusing mostly on China.
And over there,
things are a bit different.
(INSECT BUZZING)
JEREMY: Not that long ago,
China was full of old,
bent-over rice-farmer ladies,
up to their ankles in mud.
But these days,
things have changed a bit.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
As recently as the 1980s,
people here
would lie awake at night
dreaming of
having enough money...
...to buy a mule.
Whereas now,
just 30 years later,
they dream of being able
to buy a Hongqi.
Specifically this Hongqi -
the L5.
In Chinese,
Hongqi means "the red flag",
the symbol
of communism.
But there's nothing
at all communistical
about this monster's
price tag.
Which is £880,000.
The interior is
an exquisite work of art
with rosewood panelling
and cream leather.
The dashboard and centre
console are fully digital.
There's jade in
the door handles
and golden sunflowers
everywhere else.
I only saw this thing for the
first time a few moments ago
and already I'm in love.
I love the way each door
weighs the same as
a medium-sized mountain.
I love the red flags here
and on the bonnet.
I love the flagpoles.
It's like... it's like
a cartoon baddie's car,
cos in real life
nobody could be that bad.
I mean, it's impossible!
One thing the Hongqi doesn't
have is armour plating,
but even so,
it weighs
just shy of 3.2 tons.
Now to move this
enormous weight around,
it's fitted with
a six-litre V12 engine
which turns petrol
into silence.
It's not particularly
comfortable, though.
The seats especially
are very hard.
And the steering wheel
adjuster button is broken
and there are no cup holders.
And it certainly isn't fast.
In fact, it has the same
power-to-weight ratio
as a Peugeot 308 diesel.
Hongqi won't say
what the 0 to 60 time is.
I suspect because
it won't actually do 60.
You know what, though?
I don't care
about any of that,
because it is just
magnificent and evil.
(LAUGHS EVILLY)
Gloriously, brilliantly evil.
Despite its villainous
presence, though,
the price is mad.
So, I called May and Hammond
and we came up with an idea.
If you are a Chinese
businessman or
businessman-woman,
and you want a car
that reflects your status,
you don't need
to spend £880,000.
You can simply
pop over to Europe
and buy a Mercedes S-Class,
like this one.
And even though
this is the 6-litre V12,
it cost me just £8,800.
In other words, you could
have 100 of these
for the price of a Hongqi.
At this point, my colleague
Richard Hammond arrived in...
something or other.
What is that?
This is a Cadillac STS
and you can shut up.
-I wasn't gonna say anything.
-Good.
Because this is fitted
with one of the
best engines of all time.
The creamy smooth,
4.6-litre Northstar V8.
Making 300
all-American horsepower.
That engine was designed
so it can run
for up to 100 miles
with no coolant in it at all,
by shutting down one bank
of the V8 until it cools
and then the other one,
and then the other one.
That is clever.
-And front-wheel drive?
-Yeah?
It's a luxury car.
Who cares what wheels
are being driven, James?
Well, people who care
about torque steer,
weight distribution,
-dignified engineering,
doing things properly.
-All right.
I'll cancel all the track
days I've entered in it
and I'll just drive around
in it as a luxury car.
Anyway, this is the Mercedes
S-Class, which, as we know,
is really a sort of paradigm
for the luxury car
and it's a pioneer of many
things that are new on cars
and that we come to see
as standard some years later.
For example...
-first car to have...
-Soft-close doors.
How many miles has it done?
180...000.
RICHARD:
Yeah, well, I figured.
-Where did your car
come from?
-Germany.
-A German...
-Mm-hm.
...bought a Cadillac?
We were then interrupted
by the arrival of Clarkson
in a BMW.
Ooh, I see you've
bought the long car.
-Yours is long as well.
-Are you two beamed
from the 1970s?
-No, they're long-wheel base
and this is long.
-It is long.
This is the BMW 750 IL,
as Q called it in the Bond
film Tomorrow Never Dies.
JAMES: Did he?
BOTH: He did.
-Nobody told him?
-Nobody on set said,
"Desmond,
that's not what it says."
You would think,
wouldn't you? Oh, well.
And in the film,
they use 740s rebadged.
JAMES: Do they?
-Yeah. This is the real deal.
-The 5.4 litre V12.
JAMES: Hmm.
And all I paid for it
was £8,400.
That is one hell
of a lot of car.
I only paid £3,000
for my Cadillac.
That's a Cadillac.
Yes, the point I'm gonna make
is what kind of a moron
in Germany said,
"Zere's Audi, zere's BMW,
zere's Mercedes.
I should buy a Cadillac."
In fact, I know exactly.
You know those Germans
you see that think
they're Hell's Angels?
-They're dentists, but they
have Harley Davidsons.
-Yes?
And they go
to the Oktoberfest
and they drink Budweiser.
Yes, well, I know
the Germans you mean.
No, it... You're wrong.
Because the previous
owner of that car
was an American
general living in Germany.
-Was he?
-A general?
An American general
and he bought that because
he recognised what Cadillac
intended with that car,
which is to take
on Audi, BMW, Mercedes,
directly with that car
with the Northstar engine.
Oh, yes, they were
very successful with that,
Europe is full of Cadillacs.
-Yeah, you see them
everywhere.
-You never see an Audi.
JEREMY: Tripping over these.
-Rarity and exclusivity are part
of luxury.
-Let's have a look at yours.
-Mine, honestly,
is in perfect nick.
-It's um...absolutely fine.
-I saw that. I saw that.
-Saw what? Nothing to see.
-That's got double glazing
in it and has gone wrong.
Oh, wait a minute,
is your... Come on!
What's the disease?
It's got...
-James, is that
between the panes?
-Yeah, it's got mumps.
That's the most depressing -
a double-glazed window
with mildew in-between it.
-What's the matter?
-You've got mildew
inside your windows.
-Where?
-There.
-Well, it's just, it's...
-That's really poor.
Oh, my God! Basically,
it's disappearing
before your eyes.
JAMES: How can a German car...
Sure it's a real one?
Was it parked in the sea
when you bought it?
Let's not get bogged down
with the oxidisation
of my car.
Because a lot of Chinese
people, as we know,
come to Europe these days.
Mostly to go to the
Mr Shopping Village.
Which is now a bigger tourist
attraction for the Chinese
in England
than Buckingham Palace -
true fact.
-Anybody else find that faintly
depressing?
-Very depressing.
If Chinese people
are going to come to the UK
and buy Western soap
and Western frocks,
why would they not
buy Western cars
when they're there?
RICHARD: Yeah,
you can't buy these cars
second-hand over here.
-No, this vintage isn't
available here.
-No.
JAMES: No.
-Because when these cars were
new, everyone in China had...
-Bicycles.
-Yes! Or oxen.
-Yeah.
-And what we're saying is,
you can buy one of these
for a lot less than
a luxury Hongqi.
-A lot, lot less.
-And that's what we're here
to prove, people of China.
JEREMY: We couldn't have
chosen a better location
for our test -
the absolutely mind-blowing
city of Chongqing.
Let me give you a few facts
and figures, if I may,
about Chongqing.
Population in the municipal
area of around 30 million,
so it's one of the biggest
cities in the world.
14 different car makers here,
so it's China's Motown.
And it's the capital
of the Chinese
motorcycling industry.
And they made
100 million laptops
here last year.
Apparently the city is
twinned with Leicester
and you can see why.
Apart from...
everything about it.
Oh, look, a train going
through a building.
Obviously.
It's an
amazing-looking place.
The people of Dubai think
they're good at knocking up
a building quickly,
but look at the stuff
being built here.
JEREMY: Of course when a city
gets this big, this fast,
there are many ways
to make money.
There's steel
and glass
and concrete.
But one man thought,
"Hold on,
every one of the rooms
in every one of
those buildings...
..is going to need a door."
Genius.
No brainer on the Dragons'
Den, that's for sure.
It was such a good idea,
he now has
a drive-through door factory.
RICHARD: Security doors,
front doors,
interior doors...
...really
fancy-shmancy doors.
Ornate doors,
bank vault...
Car doors.
JEREMY: Five million
of them last year:
five million doors.
Well, that's not very
interesting, is it?
Yes, but now I'm
the richest man in the world.
"If employee
is angel overtime,
it is not devil
when they get salary."
OK, he's not
a brilliant writer,
but what a maker of doors!
JEREMY: The most noticeable
thing about Chongqing,
though...
...is the heat.
This is called
the furnace of China.
Average daily temperatures,
this time of year, which is,
mid-July,
45 degrees.
With 80% humidity.
This place is hot.
Like mega hot.
It's so hot and so sticky
that five minutes after
putting up a building,
the jungle
is growing out of it.
And this is OK
if you're in
an air-conditioned BMW
or Cadillac.
However...
I'm gonna have to tell you
that the air-conditioning
simply doesn't work
in my car.
Please, no. Not here.
Have you heard the news?
James's aircon.
-What?
-(MOUTHS)
Oh, dear.
-(LAUGHS)
-Oh!
Oh, that...
he's gonna feel that.
-Ho-ho!
-(LAUGHS)
JEREMY:
Aircon issues aside, though,
it did seem like we were
on to something with our
pre-owned Western limousines.
Cars here cost round about
twice as much
as they do in the UK
because of taxes and...
profiteering
from the car companies.
So if you see someone
in a Range Rover Velar
as I just did,
that here is £140,000.
Yeah, I mean, that S-Class
there, if that's a tasty one,
that's a £300,000 car
in China.
And that's why
this BMW makes sense.
You could come to Europe,
pick up a 750IL like this
for £8,500,
pay for the shipping
to China, pay the taxes,
and it would still cost you
less than a Honda Civic.
And it's not like this
is on its last legs.
I don't have a single thing
in here that's broken.
Steering wheel adjuster,
unlike in the Hongqi,
is working.
Indicators, lights, stereo -
everything. Everything works.
Windows.
I've even got
a cassette player.
Look at that.
RICHARD: All my electrics
were working too.
But actually,
in this superheated-city,
there's an even better reason
for buying a Cadillac.
When Americans build a car,
they start with the
air-conditioning unit
and then say, "Right,
let's fit a car to it.
It's top priority."
Speaking of which...
What this is, viewers,
if you were wondering,
is something called
an ice towel.
You soak it in water and
it remains cool
for up to two hours.
Borrowed it from one of
the crew. It's fantastic.
JEREMY: Eventually,
we decided to leave
the centre of the biggest
city you've never heard of.
So we negotiated
this gentleman's
sausage-shaped junction
to try our cars
on the freeway.
Where, immediately,
we had a problem.
(CLICKING)
Every few hundred yards,
there's a gantry with cameras
covering all the lanes.
And every single car
is photographed.
And every single photograph
is then analysed by...
..an official in a room
to make sure
the driver is smoking.
Because as far
as I can work out,
that is still
compulsory here.
Other things -
well, they're making sure
that you have
your seatbelt done up,
that you're not talking
on a mobile phone.
And that you're not...
Oh, how can I put this?
...touching either yourself
or your passenger.
Apparently
that's a thing in China.
Quite a few people
are prosecuted
for pleasuring themselves,
or one another,
on a long journey.
JAMES: Yes! Oh, yes.
Ohh! Oh, yes.
That is...
that's actually really nice.
Ow!
Shit, I've fanned my todger.
JEREMY: Eventually,
we arrived at the location
for our first test.
It's one of 78 centres
around Chongqing
where teenagers can learn to
drive away from the traffic.
To us, however,
it looked like a racetrack.
Which made it perfect for
an ingenious handling test
that I'd just thought of.
Now, to do this, we're gonna
use drones, like this one,
which have been fitted
with flamethrowers.
They actually use these
in China for clearing um...
litter that's got stuck
on overhead power cables.
Right. So how are we
going to use airborne
flamethrowers, like this,
to test the power
and agility of our cars?
Good question.
Each of our cars has,
as you can see,
been fitted with
three chains of firecrackers.
One on the bonnet,
one on the roof,
one on the boot lid. OK?
So you drive round
a special course here,
while you're attacked by
the airborne flamethrowers.
And then you score a point
when you've finished
for every one of the targets
that haven't gone off.
Since we were up against
two geeky millennials
and we'd be driving
powerful Western saloons,
we figured we could
outrun and outsmart
the drones easily.
♪ Flight Of The Valkyries
-(TYRES SCREECH)
-Sadly, though,
it was a massacre.
-Ah, fire from the sky!
-(FIRECRACKERS POP)
Agh! Agh!
(POPPING AND FIZZING)
(TYRES SCREECH)
-(POPPING)
-Agh! Agh!
There's the drone on my left.
The first one.
(TYRES SCREECH)
-(POPPING AND FIZZING)
-Ah, God.
God's truth!
-(POPPING)
-Ohh!
Fire everywhere.
Oh, God.
Bandit at ten o'clock.
(TYRES SCREECH)
Oh, no! Oh, shit!
-That will have alarmed him.
-It will have slightly, yeah.
-You know,
dogs don't like fireworks?
-No, they hate it.
-(FIRECRACKERS POPPING)
-Agh! Aagh! Arghh! Aaargh!
(APPLAUSE)
JEREMY:
That was such a good laugh.
Belting around
with airborne flamethrowers.
-Really good afternoon,
that was.
-Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
-What?
-Hang on.
-Yeah?
-That was
a totally useless test.
-Why was it?
-Well, we did nothing
to convince
Chinese business people
that our second-hand limos
were a good idea.
And we all scored nought.
-Yeah, and we all ruined
our paintwork as well.
-Yes, but it'll buff out.
-No, it won't.
-Well, it might.
Anyway, we shall pick
that up later on.
But now, it is time for us
to splash
in some puddles of chat...
-(LAUGHTER)
-...left by
the drizzle of debate
that falls
on Conversation Street.
(MELLOW JAZZ)
(LAUGHTER)
RICHARD: I like that one.
I like that one.
-Yeah, I know.
Damn.
We'll stick with China.
If we may.
Um...before we were allowed
to drive over there,
we all had to sit
Chinese driving tests.
Now, we've seen driving tests
around the world.
I remember one in India
I encountered once,
where a woman passed,
even though she was
in the back of the car.
And her examiner
was in another car
-following along behind.
-Yeah.
Used to be in Egypt
that you had to drive
six feet forwards,
but then six feet backwards
and then you'd pass.
-And that was it.
-I'd love to meet somebody
who failed that.
Yeah. Anyhow,
so we figured that
to get a Chinese driving test
it would be, you know,
quite an easy test.
However, we were
in for a bit of a surprise.
Now, um...I actually
got some footage
of Hammond taking his test.
-Does anyone wanna see it?
AUDIENCE: Yes!
It's poor quality, it's on
my phone, but here we go.
JEREMY:
Test centre.
Right, so he has
to ball his fists.
Then a squat. There he goes.
There he goes.
And then he has to get
on some weigh scales.
Tense moment here,
tense moment.
Still tense.
You passed!
Hammond has passed!
-(LAUGHTER)
-Seriously...
-(APPLAUSE)
-Well done.
-That was it.
-Yes!
It was nothing.
I made it look easy.
That was, well,
it was the easiest driving
test I've ever heard of.
Basically I passed because I
proved that my hands do that
and I'm affected by gravity.
-That's it.
-I think it is actually
just a test to check
that you are a human being
and not a dog.
-Cos they can't...
-Sure it was.
However, afterwards,
we were taken in
to a sort of lecture theatre
by a man who...
talked us through the perils
of the road in China.
And he said that
we had to look out
for a number of things
running out into the road,
in front of us.
Including, and I'm not -
this is a quote, yes?
You will back me up on this.
This is what he said.
Including dogs, children,
and women.
-(LAUGHTER)
-That's what he said.
-He said that.
-"Be careful,
they run out into the road."
"You never know,
they're unpredictable."
(LAUGHTER)
I don't think
the #MeToo movement
has reached
Chongqing just yet.
No. Mind you,
you say that,
there are 78 self-made
billionaire women
in the whole world.
-And 49 of them are Chinese.
-Yeah.
Well, there would be more,
but some of them
got run over.
(LAUGHTER)
Anyway, look, can we talk
about that Hongqi for a bit?
I knew you'd
want to talk about that.
-It's so you.
-It's interesting.
-It's got him
written all over it.
Bad news, though,
you can't have it in brown.
Why would I want it in brown?
-Oh, yes, you would.
-You love a brown car.
Your cars are grey
and dark green.
Mine are blue, metal fake,
red, and orange.
I can't see into your mind.
God knows
I'm not sure I want to.
But...I know James May,
as you drift off
to sleepy bobos tonight,
a brown Hongqi
will be driving...
(LAUGHTER)
"But I don't like
brown cars."
-It's like him saying,
"I love horses."
-Ha-ha.
Things that aren't true.
You love a brown car and you
can't have it in brown.
I've never had a brown car
and I am interested
in the Hongqi.
-So tell us more about it.
-OK.
Something I didn't say
in the film, which is
quite interesting,
is that when you order one,
they send a tailor round
to your place of business.
And he measures
you up for a suit
that you then wear when you
take delivery of the car.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I'd actually quite like
to be the tailor
who made the suit for you
when you take delivery
of your Hongqi.
It would have
some writing on it.
-Would it?
-Not in Chinese,
it would be in English.
Would it be a pithy
description of the wearer?
Yes, that's what it was.
It's funny you
should say that, because...
in China there's a tendency
for people to wear clothing
with English words,
you know, written on them.
They've obviously got no idea
what those words say.
I was sitting in
a traffic jam one day there
and there was a woman
on a bus next to me.
And she was
a perfectly respectable,
50-something woman
on her way obviously
to an office job or whatever.
She was wearing
a white blouse
with red flowers on it.
Now, I took a picture.
Here it is.
And what that says is,
"He was a (BLEEP) asshole."
(LAUGHTER)
I would love a picture
of her face when somebody
explained to her
what it said on her shirt.
Do you know what's really
amazing about that?
That's exactly what
I was gonna have
put on your Hongqi suit.
-She knew.
-She knew!
I wanna get back to cars,
if I may.
Because there's some truly
astonishing stats, really,
about cars in China.
We've got a graph here of
global car production, yes?
There's the UK
in tenth place.
We made 1.67 million cars
here in 2017.
Japan 8.35 million.
China, let's put it up.
RICHARD: Mind-blowing!
-24.8 million cars
they made there.
And what's extraordinary is
that you can't just buy a car
and then use it.
You have to apply to a
government-run lottery
for a registration plate
for your car.
Now here's one, OK?
In Beijing last year,
for every thousand people
who applied
for a registration plate
for a car
they intended to buy...
For every thousand
who applied,
how many do you think
actually got one?
-500.
-200.
-600.
BOTH: 300.
-Three.
-Three people?
For every thousand people
who applied,
only three actually got
a registration plate,
were allowed to buy a car.
This is good conversation,
this whole issue actually.
It's really interesting.
Would you like to guess
what was the bestselling car
in China in 2017?
Well, Volkswagen have been
there forever, so I'm
gonna say the Passat.
I'm gonna say
it's a mid-sized Hyundai
-of some sort,
sort of boxy thing.
-And you're both wrong.
It's the Wuling Hongguang.
-(LAUGHTER)
-What, that?
Yep, there it is.
That's the fella.
That's the bestselling-car
in China?
They sold half a million
of them in China in 2017.
-Really?
-Half a million
of those were sold, yeah.
They sold... Well,
half a million of...Wu...
-Wuling Hongguang.
-Those.
That's more than
the Ford Focus.
Yeah, and don't forget the
Ford Focus is sold globally.
That's just sold in China.
The car, the Chinese car,
that caught my eye,
I must say,
was the Bestune T77.
-Familiar with it?
-Oh, the Best... No.
-Never heard of it.
-No, exactly.
We've got
a picture of it here.
It looks a bit like the
Lamborghini from last week,
the Urus.
But it's much smaller, 1.2-litre
engine SUV.
All quite normal.
Except it comes
with something called
a dashboard assistant.
Which is a little holographic
figure that pops up
and you talk to it and it
helps you set the satnav
-and make phone calls
and so on.
-That's very hi-tech.
Except the little holographic
figure is of a Japanese -
a Japanese schoolgirl.
And then you can choose
what colour miniskirt
you'd like her to wear.
Got a picture...
I'm not making it up.
There's a picture here.
(LAUGHTER)
I'm not sure about that.
I'm not either, but here's
the thing, James,
the Chinese don't care
what we think, anybody.
Cos they look at us
like we look at cows.
We're just big daft things
standing around.
Only instead of milk,
we give them luggage
and watches.
(LAUGHTER)
That's actually the end
of Conversation Street.
It's not the end, however,
of the Chinese stuff.
Because we had a call the
other day from a Chinese car
manufacturer called NIO.
And they said, "We have built
a blisteringly fast,
all-electric supercar.
And would one of you
like to try it out?"
Yeah, now after his escapade
going up a Swiss hill
in a blisteringly fast,
all-electric supercar,
Richard Hammond said
that he really didn't think
he was the man for the job.
However, it turned out
that the car was only
available for one day
and unfortunately
on that day, I had the
boiler man coming round.
-Yeah. And I had
a dental appoint...
-Dentist.
Dental appointment, yeah.
Yep. So, guess what?
(GLASS TINKLING)
RICHARD: Here it is.
It's called the EP9.
And it's pretty clear
that this is no Nissan Leaf.
Because a Leaf doesn't have
giant head restraints
to stop G-forces
from snapping your neck
during hard cornering.
And that's
just the start of it.
What I have here
is a comparison
between this NIO EP9
and the Rimac Concept One,
in which I had my little,
um...
tumble down
a Swiss mountainside.
So in the Rimac Concept One,
power:
1,207 brake horsepower.
In this NIO,
1,341 brake horsepower.
Power to weight:
in the Rimac is 652
brake horsepower per ton.
In this NIO,
773 brake horsepower per ton.
Oh, good.
So, no pressure, then.
Right. The high voltage
system is active.
So here goes. To launch,
it's gotta be in drive.
-(WHOOSH)
-Left foot on brake, right
foot mash the throttle.
Right hand hold that back
for one, two, three, four,
five.
-Come off the brake.
-(ENERGY PULSES)
Urgh! (SCREAMS)
(ENERGY PULSES AND WHINES)
-(TYRES SCREECH)
-Sweet Mary Mother of Jesus!
(POUNDING TECHNO)
It's just insanity!
They say it'll do
0 to 60 in 2.7 seconds.
0 to 125 in 7 seconds.
7 seconds!
That direct, immediate power
you get from these
electric supercars
is like nothing else.
It's like one minute I'm here
and then bam! I'm over there.
It's like driving
a jet engine.
Something else about
which I have bad memories.
This is a bad place.
However, there is some good
news for people like me.
The brakes.
-(SCREECHING)
-Whoa!
That's put everything back
where it should be.
My eyes have come forward.
My lungs are
on the front again.
Oh.
Now if you want to experience
this phenomenal speed
for yourself,
you will need two things.
First of all, a lot of money.
Because this costs
£1.15 million.
Secondly, a racetrack.
Because it works like
that Ferrari FXX -
where you buy the car, they
deliver it to a track for you
along with a support team.
You drive it, crap yourself,
then they take it away
and hose it out for you.
Since it's an electric car,
you'll be wondering
about range.
Obviously if you hammer it
round a track,
you are gonna wear those
batteries out pretty quickly.
However, on the plus side,
they only take
45 minutes to charge.
On the minus side,
you have to take
the batteries out to do it.
And as they weigh
317 kilograms each,
you won't be doing that
on your own.
It is a bit more of a faff
than say, a can of petrol.
However, if you're
an electric petrol head
and you're tempted
by the NIO,
you might be
interested to know
that it's not
short of pedigree.
There's evidence that
the people behind this thing
really know
what they're doing.
For starters,
the outfit that makes the EP9
also runs a Formula E team:
one which won the inaugural
championship in 2015.
And until recently,
the EP9 itself
held a lap record
around the Nurburgring,
with an astonishing time of
6 minutes 45.9 seconds.
Which means it isn't
just about going fast
in a straight line.
(ELECTRICAL WHINE)
It has active suspension,
active aerodynamics,
torque vectoring - and all
of that means only one thing.
(THUDDING DANCE BEAT)
Grip, grippity, grip!
(TYRES SCREECH)
It has a motor in each of
the four wheels
for a four-wheel drive system
that can be monitored
and controlled constantly
by the car's on-board brain.
Add to that,
the active aerodynamics
on that vast wing
and a diffuser running
the length of the car,
it produces more down-force
than an F1 car.
(TYRES SQUEAL)
Jesus!
It's like driving an octopus.
There's no doubt that
as a piece of engineering,
the NIO is deeply impressive.
And into slingshot!
Ha-ha-ha!
But what I love about it most
is that,
thanks to its
phenomenal grip,
I could hammer it
round our track all day
and still be
the right way up.
And from me...
...there is
no higher compliment.
(LOW CHATTER)
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
Thanks for sticking me
with that.
You know, um...
it's interesting.
Watching that
has convinced me
that I will never buy
an electric car
as long as I live.
-Why not?
-Because why on Earth
would I want to employ
a team of men
and buy a forklift every time
I need to go anywhere?
Yeah, that's all very well,
but a lot of people
are more enlightened than
you, including me, in fact.
-So, Hammond?
-Yes?
Tell me, what are the...
how does it compare
with the Rimac?
-Nobody's interested.
-Yes, they are. Shut up.
The NIO, it's just, the NIO
is just more of everything.
It's more power,
more grip, more speed.
I have to say, that looked
painfully fast, that car.
It is.
It is astonishingly fast.
But it is a novelty.
An amazing powerfully
fast one, but a novelty
nevertheless.
And we should make it
absolutely clear you can't drive
it on the road at all.
-It's not road legal.
-No, you can't.
The Rimac, you can,
that's what
makes it so amazing.
And there's a new Rimac
coming out soon
that'll have more than
1900 horsepower.
But imagine the size of the
internal combustion engine
you would need
to make 1900 horsepower.
-It would be...
-It'd be massive.
That's why the future
of supercars like that
is electric.
-It is.
-What?
-It just isn't.
RICHARD AND JAMES: It is.
That's the way it's gonna go.
It's the way it is going.
OK, then, let's find out how
fast your beloved NIO
goes around the Eboladrome.
(WHOOSH)
And it's off to
the sound of the spin cycle.
Jiggling around on its
racing car suspension,
as it powers onto the Isn't.
That's exciting.
A lift and then
building up speed again.
That is looking pretty brisk.
Right, now down into
Your Name Here.
Sparks flashing off
the rear diffuser.
Torque vectoring should be
doing its stuff round here
to keep it in place.
(HIGH-PITCHED WHINE)
And now back to full voltage
for the frantic whirr
back down the Isn't.
Sounding more like
a jet fighter
and less like a Zanussi now.
OK, hard braking
for Old Lady's House.
More milk floaty noises.
And now the run
to Substation.
If it crashes here,
there really will be
a lot of sparks.
OK, two corners left.
Very tidy through there.
Just Field of Sheep to go.
Keeps it neat
and across the line.
RICHARD: That looked good.
JEREMY: She did well there.
-She did do well.
-She did well.
So exciting
with those noises.
-I like the noises.
-What? You can't like
those...
-There's a whole new set
of noises, you pillock.
-(LAUGHTER)
-OK.
-It's the future.
OK, let's see how fast your
elegantly entitled N ten,
-no, NIO...
-NIO.
-...EP9...
-Yes.
...got round, shall we?
Here we go.
JEREMY: Top ten?
RICHARD: Come on.
There you go.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yes, oh, yes!
-Come on. Come on!
-(AUDIENCE GASPS)
-Yeah!
-Yeah.
That...
That is faster...
faster than
the Aston Martin Vulcan.
You're absolutely right,
Hammond.
It is a very impressive car.
And it is faster
than a Vulcan.
But it's slower
than the petrol-powered
McLaren Senna,
which is road legal.
-So that is petrol: one...
-Yes.
Electricity: zero!
All right,
don't do that face.
Don't do that face!
-No.
-Smug face.
Not the smug face. I don't...
James,
just move it on, quick.
Yes, in this show
we are explaining
to the people of China
that they don't need to waste
huge sums of money
on new luxury cars when they
could buy something used
from Europe for a lot less.
Now so far,
we've done city driving.
We've done motorway driving.
And we've done a completely
pointless handling test
-that Jeremy devised.
RICHARD: Yep!
And now we had
to get to a rally stage
to take part in another test
that he dreamt up
whilst enjoying another
night on the pneumonia.
(LAUGHTER)
Whatever, OK.
However, listen,
before we left the
test centre where we did
the flamethrower -
the flamethrower
handling test -
we popped next door
to something called the
Zunyi Conference centre.
It was on this very spot,
in 1935,
that Chairman Mao
unveiled the plans
for the future
of his country.
This then is the birthplace
of Communism in China,
and today it stands
as an anti-Capitalist shrine.
Naturally we headed
straight for the gift shop.
-(CASH REGISTER BEEPING)
-Oh, that is exquisite.
Yes, I'll definitely have
a Chairman Mao snow globe.
RICHARD: That one.
-Oh, look.
-(WOMAN GIGGLES)
How much are these?
(CASH REGISTER BEEPS)
So that's 230.
JEREMY: It's Donald Trump.
-I'm absolutely starving.
-Yeah, me too.
-Oh, that's handy.
-That'll do.
Having paid our respects
to Communism...
...we got back on the road
in our fire-damaged cars
with James still moaning
about his temperature issues.
The air conditioning
is now so broken
that it's permanently hot,
even when I turn it to low
and press every auto button.
I decided there was only one
thing I could do about this.
Ignore him.
Jesus!
Look at that.
They're actually building
another motorway
with viaducts and tunnels
on the other side
of the valley.
You've got one motorway.
Why would you need
another one over there?
Still, all these motorways
did mean we could prove
that our cars work well,
as long-distance cruisers.
If you gloss over
the slightly worn,
interior trim on this car,
I am staggered
at how comfortable it is.
Every inch the Cadillac.
It's fitted with something
called continuously variable
road-sensing suspension.
Or suspension.
And there's more.
In Britain,
this car was described as
astonishingly reliable.
Not my words,
the words of the RAC.
The Royal Automobile Club.
The Queen herself
as good as commended
this car's reliability.
RICHARD: Meanwhile,
in the stuck record.
Lovely engine, silky smooth.
Seats are comfortable,
everything works,
except the air conditioning.
I'm running out of fuel.
There's... That's happened
very suddenly.
Er...This is May, how's
everyone doing for fuel?
I have...about
a quarter of a tank.
I'm gonna need more fuel.
The mighty North Star
has drunk it.
JAMES: Happily,
we soon saw signs
for a service station.
That's excellent. I was just
about to start panicking.
Oh.
Small problem here.
It's not open.
JAMES: So we drove
on to the next one.
Oh, thank God.
Where is it?
Where's the fuel?
Oh, it's not finished.
They could even be fuel tanks
waiting to go in.
JAMES: So, we drove on
to the next one.
Please let this one be open.
But that didn't have
fuel either.
How much money are they
spending on service stations?
Well, a lot, but they're not
earning any from them,
I can tell you that.
The problem China has is it's
building motorways so fast
that the people
building the service stations
to supply the motorway with
fuel...can't keep up.
Chaps, my fumes
are running out now.
After passing two more
unfinished service stations,
we finally got lucky.
Oh, thank God.
Ooh, that's a relief.
JEREMY: However, our
problems weren't quite over.
I mean,
is that petrol or diesel?
What... What's that?
Does green
mean petrol or diesel?
-(JEREMY LAUGHS)
-Oooh!
(WOMAN SPEAKS CHINESE)
-Oh, hello.
-How do you know
which fuel is which?
Well, we've no idea.
She just comes. This is
what she just did with mine.
-She just put that in and
I'm going, "Is it petrol--"
-(SPEAKS CHINESE)
She's putting it in
whatever it is.
JEREMY: With the lucky dip
fill-up complete,
we were ready to roll.
However, in the
RAC-approved Cadillac...
-(CLICK, BEEPING)
-Er...my car won't start.
It's the battery.
Or have you filled it up
with Ribena?
(CAR HORN BEEPING)
As the rest of China
was keen
to use this one completed
service station,
I had to push Hammond clear
of the pumps.
JEREMY: It's not really
the message we want
to be sending out to...
the people of China,
that our cars have broken.
-(CAR HORN BEEPS)
-I'm doing manual labour.
-I've found the battery.
-(BLEEP)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(ENGINE REVS)
RICHARD: Success.
JAMES: Very good.
Hammond, quite a lot
of Chinese people looking.
Well, that's the jump leads
test done.
We've done
the jump leads test.
If ever we needed them,
we can do it.
-Those Chinese-made
jump leads were excellent.
-Excellent.
Excellent.
Not that we needed them.
RICHARD:
Back on the road,
I was wondering
if the battery
wasn't the only issue.
I can't understand the
German messages on the dash,
but the engine
warning light is on.
I'll be very disappointed
if my glorious North Star
engine lets go.
It's not going to,
it's tough.
It'll be fine.
JEREMY:
In fact, we all had issues.
Chief among which was trying
to understand the road signs.
Don't "dring" when... What?
Don't "drmng" when tired.
"Drmng."
JEREMY:
Descent length surplus.
Over-speeding prohibition.
Don't drmng when tired,
again.
(LAUGHING) We've got a lot
of don't drmnging when tired.
There was another
problem too.
The roads had no drainage.
So, even in a shower...
JAMES: Look at that.
The cars on the other side
are sending fountains of
water onto this one.
Whoa.
Aquaplaning.
Holy moley.
That man's dropped...
His crash helmet's actually
come off his head.
Still, at least when it got
dark, things got worse.
(CLICKING)
Whoa! Whoa!
They'll give you epilepsy,
these cameras.
Constantly being flashed.
JEREMY: After this long
and difficult journey,
we reached
the overnight halt...
...where we were hoping
to unwind with some
relaxing comfort food.
(SIZZLING AND BUBBLING)
Holy cow, that is hot!
How... Oh, jeez.
RICHARD:
Oh...oh...
-What...what...
-That's goose intestines.
Goose intest...
Do you want some?
I've seen more
appetising things than that
stuck to the back of
my terrier.
A rub... Ooh!
...rubber hosepipe...
-Nice.
-...coated in napalm.
(BLEEP) hell!
As our mouths melted,
I brought up
another idea I'd had.
We really should be in
the back of these cars,
because...
-I agree, yeah.
-...if you're
a Chinese businessman
you're not gonna drive a car,
a 750IL or a Cadillac,
are you?
You're gonna be in the back.
Actually it's more
relevant here anyway,
isn't it?
-That's what
people care about.
-It's all they care about.
The rear seat accommodation,
leg room.
Now, Jaguar, Audi,
Mercedes and BMW
all make long cars
specifically for
the Chinese market.
So, look, why don't we...
I'm sure we could do this.
Why don't we hire some local
chauffeurs to drive our cars
and we'll ride in the back,
which is what we should be
doing.
-That's a proper place
to assess them.
-Mm, that is a good idea.
And how's this for taking it
one step further?
Why don't we, tonight,
modify our cars...
...to make them more
relevant and luxurious
for the Chinese
business community?
OK, and while we're at it,
if you two dress less like
tramps and more like
gentlemen of commerce,
the ladies and gentlemen
of China might take us
more seriously.
JEREMY: (MUFFLED)
So we've gotta get changed?
-Sorry.
-Yes.
Sorry, my whole tongue
is wrapped up in intestine.
(SIZZLING AND BUBBLING)
JEREMY: The next morning
we reconvened
after buying ourselves
some business suits.
We're supposed to be
sending out a message
that we're important,
and that people should listen
to what we have to say.
-Now I've done that.
-I think
we are doing that well.
No, I am.
No, you just look like
you've got a sub-machine gun
in a violin case.
-Have you seen James,
by the way, this morning?
-No.
No, I haven't seen
what he's gone for,
but let's be honest...
-Brown.
-Yes.
BOTH: It'll be brown.
-Nothing is more certain
than brown.
-Sombre, severe.
-Yeah.
-It's not brown.
That's not... Ohhh!
JEREMY: (YELLS)
Good morning, Vietnam!
That is bold.
Now don't pretend
you did that on purpose.
-Well, shall I be honest?
BOTH: Yes.
I ordered it using
a translation app
I got for my phone.
And you mistook
green for grey.
I don't know if I did, or
they did, or it doesn't work,
but I said "light, grey",
meaning lightweight, grey.
But I got green.
Yes, and you look ridiculous,
and nobody's going to listen
to a word you say.
The fact is, though,
we were all suited up.
So it was time to get into
the back of our modified cars
and get going.
RICHARD: What's that?
-That's one of
my modifications.
-It's Giovanni.
-No, it's Cato.
See, I ask him for something
and then he passes it
through the ski hatch.
-Absolute genius.
-It's barbarous.
Having agreed
that my manservant
was a brilliant idea,
we introduced ourselves
to our chauffeurs
and then set off.
My driver is
the excellent Mr Hoo.
I wonder
if he's a doctor, actually.
Dr Hoo is not
a particularly tall man,
but nevertheless, the space
in the back of the S Class
is fantastic.
I've got all this leg room,
I can adjust the seat.
I can recline myself a bit.
I can make myself
a bit more upright.
It's quite warm.
The air conditioning
still doesn't work. I should
actually warn Dr Hoo of that.
Doctor, I apologise, the
air conditioning is broken.
(TRANSLATOR APP
SPEAKS CHINESE)
Obviously our cars were built
before Bluetooth
and internet connectivity
had been invented.
But that's OK, because
it means you're forced to
spend your time in the back,
doing something interesting.
What I'm gonna do, instead
of watching CNN drone on
about Donald Trump,
or checking on
Nasdaq prices...
...is er...make a model...
a matchstick model
of the Eiffel Tower.
My colleagues had also
decided to make the back seat
a place of learning
and self-enrichment.
I've said many times
on this programme
how I can't cook anything
other than baked beans,
but I'm gonna use
this journey,
together with this simple
stove, this wok,
and these ingredients,
to put that right and learn
how to make supper.
I've got
my cookery book here.
Steamed razor clams with
black beans and chilli sauce.
JAMES: I, meanwhile,
had decided to try
my hand at painting.
Now this is an ideal studio
because I can paint the
things that I'm going to see
out of the window.
Sort of montage, if you like,
of typical roadside sights,
on a chauffeur-journey
through China.
Trees...
Trees right here, there.
(LIT MATCH CRACKLES)
Lovely, lovely.
(CLINKING)
Not now, Cato.
I could be sitting here
now...
...answering pointless emails
from pointless people
with nothing better to do
all day.
Not now, Cato.
But, no...
I'm doing something useful,
something joyous,
something pleasurable.
(TAPPING)
Not now, Ca... No, Cato,
no, that's inappropriate.
-(SIZZLING)
-Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Watercress.
Bit of that.
Spend enough time on
the motorway in the back
of your luxury car
and you could turn yourself
into a part-time
professional chef.
-We could improv...
-(CLATTERING)
Oh.
JEREMY:
Meanwhile, in the BMW...
Cato, my suit.
My suit jacket.
Cato, fire extinguisher.
Cato, now!
-(WHOOSH OF
FIRE EXTINGUISHER)
-Thank you. Yeah.
After a few more
mostly fire-free miles,
we pulled over
to compare our work.
May we see, James May,
what you have achieved,
instead of doing emails?
Well, it's naive.
If I were your mum or dad,
I'd put that
on the fridge door
and I'd be very proud of you.
This is going
on the wall at home.
Can we taste your soup?
Well,
you'll have to suck my tie.
That's where it all ended up.
Were you expanding your mind
by setting yourself on fire?
-Is that all you've done?
-No, no, no, no, no,
it's matches.
One snapped
and went into my sleeve.
JAMES: You've ruined
that beautiful suit.
-I wanna see
what you've done.
-Let's have a look.
I'm a bit embarrassed by it.
Is it... It's a burnt
wreck, isn't it?
It's not my best work.
This was gonna be
your birthday present,
but now you've said it's
crap you're not having it.
Please don't laugh.
Oh, right.
And you made that, did you?
-Really?
-In the back of your car.
Yeah, I know, but I...
Look... At great cost.
Yeah. Yeah.
JEREMY: For the next leg
of our journey
we tried out
the modifications
we'd made to our cars,
so they'd suit the world
of modern commerce.
Businessmen always want
a flat bed when they're on
an aeroplane,
so why wouldn't you want one
if you're in your car?
Very simple to achieve this.
Recline the front seat,
put a mattress on it,
duvet, pillow.
Take off what's left of
your jacket and into bed.
Oh, it's gone dark.
That's nice.
In the Cadillac, Hammond had
been a little more ambitious.
Name me one businessman hotel
that doesn't have a gym.
Exactly.
They all do, which is why
I've fitted my Cadillac
with this rowing machine.
So as we drive along,
I can get in shape.
Healthy body
means a healthy mind.
-How's life in your car,
Mr Hammond?
-It's brilliant, thank you.
-What about you?
-Oh, I'm just nodding off.
You go in a tunnel, it feels
like night, it's lovely.
Um... Question, though.
What's... What's James done?
I can't see him.
Bit more on the coals.
(SIZZLING)
I realise this now
looks like an idiotic idea.
It was already
a sauna in my car,
so I've built a sauna in it.
But...let's imagine you were
in the far north of China.
Let's imagine
it's the winter.
You can get through
from the other side,
through that door,
-enjoy a sauna...
-(SIZZLING)
Go back
into your car,
carry on with
your oil painting.
Ohh. Ohh.
There was, however, one small
drawback to my plan.
My driver
couldn't see his mirrors.
-(HORN BEEPS)
JAMES: Whoa! Bollocks.
-All right, all right.
-(HORN BEEPS)
God, Dr Hoo's getting
a right strop on. I know,
it's steamed up. Hang on.
-(KNOCKING)
-All right, all right,
all right.
JEREMY:
Oh, that's so nice.
Oh, that's lovely.
That is lovely,
lovely, lovely.
Mm.
Not... Not yet, Cato.
JEREMY: The next morning,
having proved that all cars
need saunas, gyms and beds,
we sacked our chauffeurs
and headed for the location
of our final challenge.
However, in the USS
Norman Schwarzkopf...
-(BLEEP)
-Geschw Grenze?
What does that one mean?
(BLEEP)
It's not well.
Oh, that's another...
I don't...
I don't know what that
warning says either.
-Oh, God, it's dying.
-(ENGINE KNOCKING)
(STEAM HISSING)
Oh, it's losing oil.
(JEREMY CHUCKLES)
What's happened?
Loads of warnings came on...
and then it lost power.
I made it to this off-ramp
and now it's... it died.
Oh, dear.
I'm not sure my jump leads
are gonna get that going,
are they?
-No.
-Oh, look.
-Oh, dear.
JAMES: That's really
gone bang, hasn't it?
RICHARD: There's oil
coming out everywhere.
Do you know the number for
the emergency services?
No, I don't.
Do you know how to say,
"My Cadillac's broken down"?
-Do you know
what junction you're at?
-No.
-Oh, dear.
-No, neither do I.
-Do you?
-No idea, no.
Come on,
we've got a long way to go.
Leaving the multilingual
Brummie to deal with the
Chinese breakdown services,
James and I got back onto
what is fast becoming...
...the eighth wonder
of the world:
China's road network.
In 1988, China had
no motorways at all.
And now, 30 years later,
it has 84,000 miles of them.
That's more than any other
country in the world.
And they're only just
getting into their stride.
Since 2011, they've been
building 6,000 miles of
motorway every year.
6,000 miles a year!
It beggars belief and it's
not like the terrain is easy.
Here, though, there ain't
no mountain high enough
and there ain't no valley
low enough, to stop them.
This bridge, for example...
...is 34 miles long.
And then there's this one,
the Duge Beipanjiang Bridge.
You could fit the London
Shard underneath it...
...twice over.
I'm telling you.
In Britain, we're doomed.
We're doomed.
We were headed, though,
for an old road,
to test the one thing
we hadn't tested so far.
And here in China, it's
the most important thing.
The thing is, luxury's all
very well, but in China,
driving is
a relatively new thing.
People have only been
doing it for 30 years.
And as is the way with all
new things, it should be fun.
Eventually we...
Well, two of us, arrived at
the location we'd selected.
It's known as
the 24-curve road
because it has
24 fun-filled curves.
It was built in 1935 to ferry
US military equipment
to China.
And it hasn't really
been maintained since.
So the surface is
loose and potholed.
And it looked like
it should be a right laugh.
This was actually part
of the road that led...
the only road that linked the
then capital of China with
India and Burma.
Yeah, well, before that,
all the supplies
that came into China
had to be flown over
the Himalayas,
which was incredibly
dangerous in the '30s.
I think the Americans
lost something like 400--
Sorry... Sorry to interrupt,
have you seen
this stupid thing?
Well, never mind that,
look what he's driving.
What, is that Hammond?
-I guess the Cadillac's
definitely broken, then.
-(JEREMY LAUGHS)
(LAUGHTER CONTINUES)
Nice!
-Check out my Fulu.
-Why have you got that?
Well I wasn't gonna let you
have all the fun, was I?
Never mind that,
why have you got it?
My telephone translation
device at the toll booth
worked to a degree,
to this extent.
What you...
Somebody got you a car?
Look, I got wheels,
three of them.
-What engine's it got?
-588cc twin-cylinder
two-stroke.
-(JEREMY INHALES)
-It's in the back.
Ah, look at that.
It's actually smaller
than its own air filter.
I was gonna say, my
alternator's bigger than
that in the Mercedes.
Anyway, listen.
Here's what we're doing.
-Yeah.
-It's a test of speed.
Cos we are against the clock,
bear that in mind, OK?
And durability,
at the same time.
So you've gotta get
up this road,
which goes all
the way up there,
as fast as possible,
and keep your car
in one piece in the process.
Richard and I decided
that James
should volunteer to go first.
Oh.
Oh, you look exactly
like a racing driver,
apart from visually.
It's a racing clown.
Can we just get on with it?
It's very hot in here.
Going with your window
down or up? Lot of stones.
Down?
It's a small risk
from being hit by a stone.
It's a large risk of
dying from suffocation.
Right. Anything else
we wanna say to him?
Yes. "Go."
Just take some time
and prepare mentally,
and really think about this.
-Have you visualised
the course?
-No.
RICHARD: OK.
JEREMY: He looks quite cross.
RICHARD: He does, yeah.
-Three, two, one, go!
-There you go.
Push.
Oh ,God, I can't...
I can't see round
right-hand bends because
of my sauna.
Whoa!
Massive hole there.
I've just realised that
I've only been comfortable
for 20 minutes
of this entire trip.
My car's been too hot,
my suit's too hot,
now the road's too rough.
Bit of squirrelling there
from the broken traction
control.
The finish line!
I've done it!
JEREMY: Next, it was my turn.
Right, I'm attaching the
wobbly-headed symbol
of Capitalism here,
to bring me good fortune
on this perilous test.
-If you're ready.
-Yes.
Five, four, three...
(LAUGHS)
...two, one.
Go!
Now, I'm guessing James May
will have gone for caution.
I'm not going to.
Cos I'm going
for speed and power.
And then just trust
in the BMW build quality.
My wobbly-headed symbol
of Capitalism is wilting.
It's not... Arrrgh!
Jesus, that was
a big tail slide there!
Oh, yeah.
Stick it in here. Oh, yes.
-(RATTLING)
-Oh, what's happened?
(RATTLING AND CLANKING)
Yeah.
-You overdid it, didn't you?
-Yeah.
JAMES: So I've won that.
Well, we don't know.
We haven't got your time yet.
You said - your words: "Test
of durability and is against
the clock."
Your car is broken.
-It's not broken,
a tyre's come off.
-It's broken.
RICHARD:
Down at the start line,
I was waiting
for the signal to go.
Hm. Little cubby hole.
JEREMY: Richard Hammond.
Hello, yes.
JEREMY: Three, two, one, go!
-Oh, come on, I'm not...
Right, OK, here I go.
(ENGINE REVS)
And we're off.
Oh, Christ! Oh.
I am limited on power.
Top speed: 39 miles an hour.
Ow, ow!
We're never gonna get an air
ambulance in here, are we?
Well, he might
have a very long winch.
Ohhh!
Big drops, I don't like that.
Ow!
Nervous of hill
climbs these days.
Agh, oh.
A line, use my line.
Ow.
Oh, my God!
Oh, dear!
Oh, God!
-Did anyone s...
-Was that...
-Did he just crash it?
-Was that a crash or did he
just disappear behind the...
He has, look,
he's gone off there.
Er...so there we are,
I'm afraid that
Richard Hammond's luck
has finally run out.
And it's with deep regret,
and great sadness,
that James and I
must now announce
the untimely demise of...
RICHARD: I'm all right.
-Not again.
-How's he do it?
I don't know.
Well, on that terrible
disappointment,
back to the tent.
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
-Look at my face.
-I'm OK. I'm OK.
JEREMY: Smug face.
-I'm fine.
-Don't worry.
-Smug.
Smug because I won that.
-No, you didn't.
-I did, I was the fastest.
And it was supposed to be a
test of fun and you moaned
the entire way up the hill.
It was a test of durability.
You had to change a wheel
and where's the fun in that?
Well, I wasn't the idiot that
put a sauna in my car.
What's wrong with a sauna?
Because in every hotel
that's got a sauna,
the corridors are
always full of wet idiots
with those slippers
that don't fit.
-Hello? Hello?
-What?
I did have quite a big crash
at the end there. I thought--
There's nothing particularly
remarkable about that,
is there?
I mean, why would you...
The fact is,
the reason you crashed...
Well, obviously
you're incompetent.
But also because your
Cadillac broke down and
your Mercedes was too humid.
So that means
the winner is definitely,
of the whole thing,
the BMW 750i.
-What?
-Actually, no.
To be fair, the real winner
of the whole thing was
our brilliant idea
to sell second-hand limos
to the Chinese.
No, he's absolutely right
about that,
because it makes them happy
and it helps us with
our balance of payments.
-Everybody wins.
-It was a good idea.
-Yes.
-Except for one tiny detail.
You see, this programme
is shown in every single
country in the world.
Except one.
(LAUGHTER)
-Which one?
-China.
Ah.
So this entire show has been
a total waste of time.
It's an hour of your life
you'll never get back.
And on that terrible
disappointment,
it's time to end.
Next week, I'm happy to say,
we're back in the groove.
We're in Scotland and I get
an Alfa Romeo GTV6,
make me very happy.
See you then, take care.
Good night.
-Good night.
-(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)