What can you see, Egle?
Nothing good.
Illness.
No.
Poison.
Poison, here at the Wawel castle?
Who do they want to poison?
Look, Egle, and say!
I can't see anything more.
But take care of yourself and the girls.
This house isn't safe.
Maybe I should have left with my brother.
But then they won't put
the crown on your head.
I'm not fleeing anywhere.
People say she's a witch.
Really? Maybe I'll ask he
to cast a spell on you.
So that you want and love me.
Are you a wife that deserves love?
You bring your brother to defend you?
From whom? Me?
He's your ally, like the
whole of Lithuania.
You wrote to your brother in secret.
Hiding from me.
Is this how a loyal and
faithful wife behaves?
And you didn't tell me
of the king's illness.
Is this how a loyal and
faithful husband behaves?
And the lie that the king
went into a retreat...
Are you surprised I wanted to check this?
Sneaking out of the castle in disguise?
Am I your wife or prisoner?
No, only not the nutmeg.
This may remind the king of
the mutiny of bishop Muskata.
Bake bread with honey and spices.
We have to receive the family honourably.
My lady, maybe we ask the
bishop for dispensation?
So that the guests don't feel offended?
Are we to be embarrassed with
our piety, observance of Lent?
Don't change anything
and, just in case, get rid
of this Lithuanian cook.
We need extraordinary caution.
No stranger is allowed in the kitchen.
This is fine, but without dressing.
And this too.
Maybe I could hire someone for help?
No, it's too dangerous.
So, maybe let the Lithuanian stay.
She's very devoted to her
lady, princess Anna.
And, last but not least, a Christian.
A Christian, you say?
If you vouch for her, then fine.
I heard you're looking for
a job in the Wawel Castle.
Where do you know it from?
Bring it to the castle.
What is it?
Spice.
Find someone else for errands.
I'm looking for a better job.
Do it well and I'll help
you get a better job.
You'll put it there and that's it.
Be fair, Anna.
I wasn't here because I was in Hungary
and then at war for a long time.
I'm constantly at war.
With your mother.
She talks about mercy and has sin
in her mind because she hates...
Mind your tongue!
I never neglected my duties as your wife.
And you, good lord, how many women
have you had since we married?
How often and how passionately
do you express you love to me?
Do you want war with me?
No, I only want you to treat me fairly.
The Czechs are preparing to capture Krakow.
The Teutonic knights are
standing at the border.
The Hunchback and Przemysl are
only waiting for my father to die
to remove me from power.
In such moment I can't have your
brother behind my back, I can't!
Do you know why he came here?
Because he worries about us.
About me, but also about you.
Cousin?
Laudatur lesus Christus.
Prince, you're alone, without retinue?
Alone. We're rushing to uncle Vladislav.
Your visit is a great
honour to our monastery.
My people are staying in the Miechow Forest,
and they can enter the Wawel Castle any time.
Every day we pray for king Vladislav
for peace in our land and for unity.
Very well, we're just passing
on the way to Krakow.
But first, we need to pray for
the success of your plans.
You'll send Algirdas back.
But understand, we can count only on him.
He's not helping but only
putting you in danger.
Don't you understand
what our council means?
You're a thorn in my mother's side.
We were to pave Lithuania's way to Rome,
and how did it end?
Together, we're fighting
against a Christian order.
What kind of Christian order is that?
Plain murderers with
crosses on their capes.
But Christian...
The bishop is only waiting
for your false move.
He'll accuse you of
godlessness and paganism.
You wouldn't let it happen,
would you, my husband?
So, you would...
The Czech king is spreading such rumours.
He's got the title to the Polish crown
so he wants to get it at all cost.
The Czech one seems not enough.
There's danger lurking from any direction.
The future king isn't afraid, is he?
The future king isn't afraid of anyone.
But he's never blind to
what's going on around him.
Dear Anna.
Hey, where are you bringing it?
To the Wawel Castle's kitchen.
I'll help you.
I won't pay homage to Casimirus.
Our duchies could connect Greater
Poland with Lesser Poland
On condition the crown
is yours and not his.
This would be best for you and for me.
I don't know, Przemyslav,
our families have always
been loyal to Vladislav.
Times have changed.
What are we to do?
Kuyavia is lost.
Teutonic knights set the terms.
Maybe there was no other way.
If only the king had wanted,
there would be a way.
We can't allow Casimirus's coronation.
The mass is just starting.
We're hurrying to Krakow.
Can there be anything more urgent
than a prayer to our lord?
So similar, almost like the king...
Who's this?
King's oldest grandson.
Bolko Swidnicki. He stopped
Jan of Bohemia's army.
Why is he here?
Have the Czechs invaded again?
Maybe the king opened his eyes
and understood his son is not
suitable to be his heir.
Because he can't fight but
only slay, like in Koscian.
Quickly, quickly!
- Where to put it?
- Here!
Yes, according to the deal.
And what are you doing here?
Somebody said you need help in the kitchen.
We don't need anybody. Get out!
Mum!
At last!
It's good you summonned me. How is Father?
A bit better. He wanted
to see you all together.
- Take a rest.
- Thanks God, he's alive!
Bolko, my son, has come with me.
To celebrate his victory over the Czechs,
I ordered new pearls for Holy Mother.
- Here you are.
- I'm so proud of my son.
Does Father know the Czechs
want to take his crown.
They're writing letters all the time.
They say Poland doesn't exist anymore.
And that Father is the king of Krakow only.
But these are only words...
They say everywhere it's true...
You'll tak about it with Father
and consult Casimirus what to do next.
Yes...
Does anything bother you?
Do you want to tell me something?
I'm your mother, don't hide anything!
Mother...
Bolko has already some experience.
He's clever, brave, mature...
That's why we admire him...
And there are different
opinions about Casimirus.
Kunegunda, listen...
I'm very proud of my grandson and your son,
I believe when Casimirus
sits on the throne,
he can rely on him.
If you gave your son some
hopes for the crown,
talk to him before he meets Casimirus.
You know your brother's temper...
And take this too, quickly.
Good day, Bolko!
Good day, I see Krakow is
growing with every day.
I'd like this city to be the capital
of all our duchies one day.
The capital of Poland.
Yes, if only the Czechs
wouldn't take it from us.
You defeated Jan once, so I believe
you'll do it again if necessary.
I'm proud of you, Bolko.
We'll meet at the king's chamber.
You must leave.
Your presence is not helping me.
Algirdas, they're accusing
me of still being a pagan.
I'll kill your Casimirus like a dog!
The news of his antics in
Visegrad reached even Lithuania.
He raped a maidservant of queen Elizabeth.
And then they had her family
killed to the third generation.
And he has the nerve to
accuse you of anything.
It's not him.
He only complains I didn't give him a son.
Everybody gossips little
Kunegunda isn't his
because he was sick after
little Elizabeth's birth.
And you're tolerating this...
You let yourself be humiliated...
Accused...
Don't you have dignity?
Aldona...
Do you want this crown so much?
I'd take you even today.
To the Neman River. You'd
be free, think about it?
You'll come back to your people.
Here, they forbid you to dance, have fun...
This is not a castle for you.
This life is not for you.
This is my husband and
these are my children.
And this is my land now.
You have to help Casimirus.
Everybody will be against him.
That's why he needs to seek allies.
Has everybody come?
Are there my daughters?
Nephews?
Vladislav of Leczyca and Przemysl
of Sieradz haven't arrived yet.
Also, we've got no news from Elizabeth.
Our envoy to Hungary hasn't returned yet.
I wanted to say good bye.
Dominus vobiscum.
Et cum spirit tuo.
What have you got?
A letter to the king.
To the king?
In person.
It's not the good time
to send anybody there.
It's got the Hungarian queen's seal.
I'll take you to the queen.
I was told to give it
to the king in person.
The lady will decide if
you can see the king.
No one can enter.
The king's council is in session.
Castellan of Krakow will summon you, lady.
It's the king's order.
Maybe they're deciding
you won't be the king.
So this is what you want?
Kunegunda, your brother will be the king.
If they start the war
with the Teutonic knights
he won't be the king because
Poland will cease to exist.
Give way, I advise you.
I don't feel good that I leave you here.
I'll take care. Don't worry.
Give my greetings to everyone.
Everyone?
You'll give him a son, and
they won't touch you.
Stay well, sister.
You'll help him.
You'll help Casimirus.
Help him become great.
My lord,
you can count on me.
Father!
King!
Vladislav!
Father!
Look who's come to you!
Your beloved daughter.
And your grandson.
Vladislav?
King?
So, it's begun...
I've been looking for you.
Where have you been, my lady?
What's happened?
And why are the bells tolling so wildly?
King Vladislav died.
A Lithuanian will be the queen of Poland.
So that he won't pick
somebody from the living.
Husband, I'll summon our daughters.
Knight! I have to speak to the king!
Help me, I have a letter to the king!
It's a pity, my lady, you
don't have a son to lean on.
I have daughters, who love their father.
Don't you think, my lady, it's God's gift?
Where are the royal stables?
There, my lord.
My lady, a Clarisse nun
is waiting with a letter
from your sister Elizabeth,
the queen of Hungary.
Ask her in.
Forgive me, lady, it can't wait.
The king has to read it
as soon as possible.
Give me the letter.
I was clearly instructed -
only to the king's hands.
Here they are.
Where is the chamberlain?
He was to take the girls.
I'm Kunegunda, and you?
Kunegunda!
Mom, they're so alike!
What does it mean?
Who is it?