I may not eat meat
but I really missed horse riding.
Not only you, but we have
to follow the rules.
You can change them,
you'll be king soon,
actually, you're king already.
If the king doesn't follow the law
he becomes a tyrant.
This is the only thing
I'm really afraid of.
I've seen a lot of pride
among those who rule,
and I don't want to be like this.
You won't. You're different, you're free.
Lent is over.
We buried Father. Let's
hold a feast, at last!
You know how Mother will react
when she hears of dances.
- Another quarrel...
- There will be another quarell, whatever.
She doesn't need a reason.
Let's wait till the coronation.
And then, will it be different?
/praying in Latin/
How do you think?
Is it my fault little Elizabeth fainted?
She's a child and she fasted like an adult.
I shouldn't have taken her to give alms.
Mum, it's not your fault.
The weather's so changeable
and she's so sensitive...
Mother?
What happened?
Little Stephen... was the same as she.
My firstborn son...
We've never talked about it.
Never.
Pity, isn't it?
I still can see... the
faces of my dead children.
Shall we pray together?
And you?
I'll pray for you.
I'll pray my whole life.
Not whole!
One day you'll get married
and have a lot of duties.
No, queen aunt, I'll go to
monastery, I won't get married.
Mum is always sad and it's
so beautiful in church.
Elizabeth, but marriage is very important,
you'll have children, and you may
even be the ruler of a kingdom,
like me or aunt?
But I don't want. I'll pray
for Dad, that is, the king.
And for Poland.
What's going on?
Nothing.
I can see you're hiding something.
No.
I talked to Algirdas at the hunt,
and he worries about you
he says you look lost.
Let's leave them.
If they need us, they'll find us.
Or we'll find them.
They didn't even leave
one bowl in one piece.
The stole all baskets and hares.
Everything I bought from
Hungarian merchants.
Hides, sacks, belts, wine skins...
They stole everything.
God, for what sins do you
punish me like this?
And there? Two barrels
with cabbage were hidden.
They sniffed them and stole them.
There were dried mushrooms here.
Nothing's left.
I'll help you, Rose.
And everything I collected
at the king's funeral.
Big purchases attract thieves.
I heard the inn-keeper
is looking for workers.
Am I to serve beer to the drunkards?
I'm sorry, Rose, I only wanted...
What did you want? Did you want
me to be a servant at the inn?
I only wanted to help, Rose.
God forgive you such advice.
I'd better go.
What's biting you?
He should know when you work for yourself,
you don't want to be somebody's servant.
But he meant well. You should go
to the castellan. He's a just man.
- What for?
- With request, as a victim of thieves.
You'll make a complaint and
maybe you'll get something.
The castellan should know
there's banditry in town.
Where's Aldona?
Gone for a ride.
In such weather? There's
going to be a storm!
Little Kunegunda and Yolanta
are quarreling again.
You need to understand Yolanta.
She experienced a lot.
A savage...
She says little but she can scream.
I think she needs a mother.
I feel nobody cares about her.
It's true. The kid doesn't understand
you're on your own in the world.
I'd be happy to take care of her, but...
I'm afraid to ask.
It can't be like this. We
need to talk to Aldona.
Anna.
I don't want to go back to the castle.
It's so gloomy there.
It's not easy for the girls either.
First, the grandfather's death, then
the whole affair with poison.
I worry about them,
especially little Elizabeth.
Admit it, Yolanta's on your mind.
Will you ever tell me who her mother was?
She's dead. Isn't it enough?
I don't want to revisit the past, but
I won't send her back to monastery.
The Hungarians were executed.
There's no danger anymore.
They were not alone. We
don't know who helped them.
There's an inn over there.
The poorest of your
subjects must eat better.
Excess at the castle hurts the subjects
when the country's ruined by war.
Your highness, I have a letter from
his majesty king Charles Robert.
Maybe they've discovered
other conspirators...
Let me open it, Mother.
Bad news?
The pope fainted during a mass.
Well, he's almost 90 years old.
He nominated three cardinals, Frenchmen.
So, again Frenchmen are going
to elect the next pope?
My husband asked me to pass
his respects to Mother.
Tell him I pray for him.
You witnessed the execution, didn't you?
Did they say anything before they
died, did they turn anybody in?
Even when tortured, they
only cursed his highness.
They said he's got enemies, in Poland too.
Are you hiding something? I've
got no secrets from my mother.
That's all I know.
Anybody rising against my son
will be severely punished.
I believe, by God's decree, he'll be king.
They're robbing again.
Those merchants lost everything.
They even stole peasants' herbs.
In Krakow it's the same story.
My acquaintance, a stall
holder, was robbed too.
I'm looking for a job for her...
No! I wanted to hire somebody
but I have nothing to pay now.
I'll be broke myself soon.
People have nothing to pay with.
Today I've only sold two fishes
and three bowls of groats.
I can't afford it.
Say, how to live?
And even this rain...
Lightnings, the end of the world.
One beer, please.
A moment.
I told you the castellan's not here.
So, who'll listen to my complaint?
Help, good people, help!
What's going on?
Let go!
Sire, I came to see the castellan.
He's said to have gone
to the Teutonic knights.
He's not in Krakow.
So, who's going to help me?
I'm only a stall holder.
My husband drowned.
Such misfortune! They took everything,
even the last piece of cheese.
Calm down! Who and what
did they take from you?
They must be pagans because
it was a holy day.
I fasted on Good Friday, and today too.
Today it's because I have
nothing to eat anyway.
On Easter they burgled my
house and took everything.
I'll pass it to the castellan
and he'll take care of it.
Will I get back even a little?
Come in a fortnight.
He'll hear you out.
Sir, I beg you, give me something to eat.
How can I pay you if I was robbed?
Where will I take goods
from if I give them away?
At least give me something to drink, man!
Fine.
Here.
God bless you, sir.
May God be with you, inn-keeper.
May God be with you, my lords!
Go away!
Sit down, please!
Sit down please!
Serve us your best food! Quickly!
Yes, sir! I'm on it! The best!
It must be some great lord.
It's raining.
It's not safe here.
What do you think of sending Anna
with the girls to the north?
Maybe Sandomierz.
- Mum! - Yes?
You shouldn't separate
Casimirus from his wife.
Who's talking about separation?
It's all about her feeling safe.
And I can be free here and
take care of politics.
All you want is to keep the crown.
Maybe.
All I want is that all is well
for our family and, first
of all, for the new king.
I hope Casimirus took a
warm kaftan and cape.
Coming, my lords, here you are...
God bless you.
Pardon my insolence, your highness
May God be with you.
I'm begging you, my
acquaintance was robbed.
The woman's left with nothing.
She's left alone and without help.
My lord, help ordinary folk.
Thieves are spawning everywhere,
on roads, in towns, it can't be!
You impressed me you
don't ask for yourself.
Who are you?
I'm a potter. I do the best I can.
- What's your name? - Joseph.
I was brought up in Pradnik.
Inn-keeper!
How much is in our purse?
Yes, sire!
Today, you'll feed everyone hungry.
Whatever you have.
Yes, sire!
Who is it?
Man! This is king Casimirus!
Lady, there's only beer, very poor.
Your highness, can we enter?
Sure. Amadeus, bring in the gifts.
This is for you.
Thank you.
And this is for you.
Yolanta, you'll get something special.
This rosary was blessed
by the pope in Avignon.
It's treasure.
Let it lead you in your life.
Queen Aunt, I'll be happy
to exchange, may I?
I prefer a rosary, and I see Yolanta's sad.
May everybody have a heart like you.
I also have a great request to you.
Ask Grandma to let me learn to write.
I'd really like to!
Now?
St. Felix wrote letters
to the emperor at my age.
Potter!
My wife has a request to you.
You'll make beautiful bowls
and jugs for our castle.
Lady, I will! Whatever I can.
The coronation's coming.
An important day. There'll be may guests.
I'd like more such beautiful
things to be at the castle.
I don't know if I'll manage, lady...
Come to Wawel.
My sister queen Elizabeth's
people will show you new styles.
It's great honour!
But remember!
I don't want them to be the
same as Hungarian or Venetian.
I want them to be colorful
and decorative, but ours.
Polish!
And let this acquaintance
of yours help you.
Yes, sire!
Forgive me, sire, another
guest has recognized you.
Can they come closer?
Come people!
King! We thank you!
God, if you leave people no other
choice, this must mean only one thing.
That you summon them, do you?
I had a bad husband.
Drunkard, but he was mine.
The Vistula River took him from me.
If they hadn't robbed me,
maybe I could make it.
If God allowed...
But He didn't...
Maybe it never rains but it pours...
And God has nothing to do with it.
Jesus!
Rose, for God's sake!
and then the people knelt and
the whole inn started shaking...
and Casimirus only looked humbly...
Cudka, he's... really great.
You should see the beautiful dresses
queen Elizabeth brought for the girls.
And, imagine, little Elizabeth
gave hers to Yolanta
because she wasn't given a dress
but a rosary, and she was sad.
What did queen mother say?
She doesn't like when the girls dress up.
Yes, but they were so happy!
It was joy to see it.
Cudka... you like children, don't you?
I'd like to care of orphans.
When I see Yolanta my heart breaks.
I won't thank you. Don't expect it.
I don't want you to thank
me but to find a job
which you may like.
If you helped me with my jugs,
it would be much easier.
I'm good at trading, not craft.
You'll learn soon.
Just for a start to help you
stand on your own feet.
I've got a big order from the king.
I won't manage just by myself.
But on the very holy day...
Easter!
I went to the office and what?
It's not fair!
But the king is. And his wife, Anna, too.
When I told them about you, they
placed an order immediately.
I told them!
God bless you!
Casimirus, I have a request to you.
Write to the chancellor and...
he'll consider it.
Oh, say it out!
Will you agree that I get married?
Sure, Niemierza, this is great news!
With Cudka.
What do I have to do with it?
You've got to ask Pelka.
But I want to have the king's blessing.
You've got it, of course!
We'd also like to...
adopt Yolanta.
She'd be close to you,
and she'd have a family.
I'm sorry, I didn't want to disturb you.
I just mean well.
I know you're doing it for me
and you don't need help at all.
- But... - Don't interrupt!
It's nice you do it for me.
I'm poor. No one at all
would pay attention to me.
I will work with you.
And your potter's shop will be...
not only the best in the whole street...
but in the whole kingdom!
If, of course, it's true about
this order from the king.
Because I won't believe
you met him face to face.
I'll save money, and I'll order
beautiful votive offerings for Martin.
The most beautiful in Krakow.
For my little Martin...
Casimirus!
Where are you?
The first night in the king's chamber.
It's a bit creepy here.
Niemierza asked to give him
consent to marry Cudka.
And? Did you agree?
I won't stand in the way of love.
You can't!
Cudka's afraid to ask me, but I see
she'd like to take care of Yolanta.
Let them get married, but I
won't let them take her.
I see everything starts to turn out fine...