Didn't Aldona want to come?
It's not surprising my sister
is suffocating at Wawel.
Did she complain?
She's missing Lithuania.
We don't invite women to hunting.
We hunt on our own.
Without women.
This is her home, but her heart...
Be kind to her.
So, you've given dispensation, after all.
Easter is coming, so we need meat.
I heard a bear plundered royal beehives.
Isn't it the same one that
escaped during your last hunt?
Insult!
Why to pierce such a valuable hide?
You should leave it for better hunters.
Don't be misled by who I am.
I know how to use the weapon.
And the tongue.
I will hold a mass for the hunting.
Maybe under this big oak?
We don't pray under oaks. We're not pagan.
What I meant was shade.
So, maybe I'll get this bear.
But don't worry. You'll get
some lard as consolation.
You'll rub it in your back, bishop.
/praying in Latin/
Anna, why aren't you praying?
We're sitting in these vaults all the time.
The body fragments are creepy.
Don't say so, these are holy relics.
Why couldn't I go hunting with them?
I can use a bow better than any of them.
Because none of them is a
wife of the heir apparent.
You keep complaining you feel confined,
but when I go to give alms, only
little Elizabeth accompanies me.
I'm leaving.
Why?
Won't you wait for the coronation?
No, mother.
Go in peace. The mass is ended.
You're holding the bow like
a woman holds a sliver.
You need to hold it like a woman.
Tight and tender.
You want to challenge me?
You want to ridicule yourself?
Ready!
Two shots.
Like children...
No Pole can shoot as well as a Lithuanian.
Except for me.
How about further?
Haven't you heard the best
bowmen are from Krakow?
I haven't heard you're one of them.
What happened?
I'm barely alive.
Today, I did these three Hungarians who
wanted to poison the royal family.
The first one was easy, the second one
fainted immediately, but the third one...
He groaned like hell, and
in damn Hungarian...
There was nothing left to break...
You should have killed them faster.
Hadn't it been for Casimirus's
servants, I'd have killed them.
But the order was to
give them painful death.
They were to beg for mercy.
Did they?
And why are you so curious?
Do you think it's fun to torment people?
Then you have such
nightmares that it hurts.
Especially the heart.
I have such nightmares and backache...
So, go see the medic, maybe he can help.
Thank you, I'd rather stay alive.
Last time he wanted to burn warts
on my hands with hot iron.
And they say it's me who
doesn't have mercy.
On top of it, I am to kill
my relative's husband.
I don't feel sorry for him
because he's a scoundrel.
Still, family is family.
Why have you dressed up like this?
I'm going to see the king.
The king's gone hunting.
So, the queen.
I won't let you torture my Martin.
Did I tell him to bring poison to Wawel?
He didn't even share the money
he got for it with you.
He drank it away himself.
His conscience didn't let him calm down.
He's always been sensitive.
Are you talking about the same man, or
maybe you've got two different husbands?
You never liked Martin, did you?
Don't be so happy. I won't
let my man get killed.
I'll beg the queen and God.
You'll return to Krakow in the evening,
take somebody and go to the Great Master.
Maybe we should wait for their answer
after their envoy returns.
We need to renew the truce
as soon as possible.
We can't afford a new war.
People are tired. They need peace.
I want them to feel safe.
And make sure bishop Jan
doesn't know about it.
He's very stubborn in the Teuronic case.
The later he gets to know
about it, the better for us.
Don't you know my opinion?
You'll move out tomorrow at dawn.
You've always valued my opinion.
I need to start ruling at last.
Greetings. We've been to
Tyniec for a retreat.
And we were told you're hunting here.
Forgive our hard words.
We didn't want to stand against you.
We just have a different view
on the country's affairs.
I bear no grudge.
We'd like to attend your coronation.
Now we have to stick together, don't we?
Here.
Thank you.
Bring it there.
God bless you.
You're a saint, lady. Like
your mother and sisters.
Thank you.
Elizabeth!
Where's bishop Grot?
He was to wait for us here.
He was just ahead of us.
He went further to get the bear first.
It's the bishop's horse.
I hope the bear didn't get him.
Elizabeth, darling, look at me.
Egle, go away, no sorcery!
Anna, how can you allow this?
It's only herbs, lady,
like yours from Tyniec.
Oregano and valerian.
It won't end well, let's call a medic.
- Mum! - Easy, darling!
I'll go to the kitchen and
tell them to bake apples.
I won't eat apples, Egle. I'm fasting.
What have you said?
I haven't been eating for three days.
St. Kinga at my age did penance and fasted.
It's important, isn't it, grandma?
Are you happy?
This is the result of your teaching.
Did you tell your chldren
to do penance and starve?
I'm not surprised only
three of them survived.
Forgive me.
You left me no choice.
I shouldn't have said that, I'm sorry.
Do you really hate me so much?
You were so young when you came here.
I thought I'd be able
to be a mother for you.
You've never even tried.
I've been trying every day.
You wanted to get rid
of me on the first day.
The king persuaded me.
But you don't make it easier.
We have only one thing in common.
Taking care of the girls and Casimirus.
Not only did I miss the hunting, but
now I need to go back with you.
In a carriage, like a woman.
Bolko, bring me to Wittenberg...
to Rudolf.
Son...
You haven't changed your mind?
I'm asking you for the last time.
Come with us.
Casimirus needs me.
I'm sorry for Anna.
Nothing matters to you except
Casimirus and this rim of gold.
You're not fair.
Mum.
Some woman's begging to see the queen.
I almost shot you, what happened?
An adder scared my horse.
Or your god got angry that you
want to shed blood in Lent.
I gave dispensation for the whole hunting.
All candles in Krakow churches
are made from these hives.
We can't allow some bear to destroy them.
Come on.
Are you afraid someone can see you
on the same horse with a pagan?
You can say that all the way
you were evangelizing me,
and my horse too.
Quiet!
A bear?
Rather a human.
Have mercy on my husband.
He didn't deserve death in torment.
There's no mercy for those who rise
against the king and his family.
There isn't and there won't be.
He's not evil, but foolish.
God didn't distribute
brains among people evenly.
I can't release him.
You're the queen, lady.
You can do everything.
The law is the law and
it binds the queen too.
Let go! I need to talk to your commander.
Go to hell!
Somebody else should be sitting here.
She deserves painful death, not me!
Understand?
The truth is I told him to look for a job.
He got in this mess because of me.
I should be in the vault now, not him.
It's my fault.
This woman has no conscience.
She told me to bring poison to the court.
She said it's spice. How
could I know it's poison?
Why are you telling me this only now?
I was to take the whole truth to my grave.
But how could I die with clear conscience
knowing she still walks the earth.
I love her more than anyone.
But, for money... this woman
is ready for the worst crime.
It's only words.
I've got a proof.
I know where she hid the money
she got from the Hungarians.
So, speak!
I will!
Of course, I will.
But on one condition.
Have you called for me, lady?
By my decree, Martin Harcik
will be only beheaded.
Without the torture he was sentenced for.
But I already sealed the king's
and the chancellor's will.
Do as I say.
When the king is absent, I rule here.
God bless you, lady!
Take her.
Where have you been, sire?
I sent ten people to look for you.
I found your bishop and this kid myself.
He's a poacher.
You know it's a royal forest.
Where are you from?
From beekeper's post by the river.
Go bring his father.
My father's dead.
The Teutonic knights killed everybody.
I'm the oldest man in the family.
Do you know the punishment for poaching?
I'd rather hang than
watch my sisters starve.
Wouldn't you rather have a job at the
castle and money for their upkeep?
You can't. He was poaching
at your property.
He broke the law!
I won't hang a kid. He's even
younger than my little Elizabeth.
What's your name?
I was baptized as Maciek.
Come to the royal kennel.
There's a job for you there.
Now go. Didn't you forget something?
Lady, please excuse me.
The timing may not be the best,
but I have a big request.
Will you speak out for me with my father?
I don't think you really
need my backing, Helen.
A heart matter?
My knight is Jasko, the son of Spytek.
And I am from Poznan.
My father and brothers will
never agree to our marriage.
I'm not allowed to even look at him.
I can't imagine my life without Jasko.
Lady, excuse the interruption.
Marcin Harcik claims the whole
conspiracy is led by his wife.
That's impossible.
He swears on his head it's true.
So he'll lose it!
He'll be beheaded but without torture.
How come? Why?
I pardoned him on his wife's request.
I haven't seen a woman who loved her
husband so much for a long time.
She was even ready to let herself
be locked instead of him.
And this coward accuses her and
blames her for everything.
My children were almost
killed because of him.
Don't forget they wanted to poison me too.
What shall we do, then?
Proceed with beheading and that's all!
But he was sentenced for death by torture.
Thanks God you don't rule here.
Let me go!
Calm down! I won't torture
you, one blow and that's it.
And is that to calm me down, cousin?
Mind that my axe may miss the right spot!
Harcik, get up!
Go, get water!
What's with the water?
Lazy dogs!
Guards, catch the runaway!
Tak off your clothes or I'll kill you!
Have mercy, sir!
Now!
Don't look! Take off your clothes!
Quickly!
Run!
Guards!
Who are you?
There, in the river. Somebody's drowning.
This must be our runaway.
Save him, sir!
You save him!
I can't swim.
Let's check it.
Have you seen anybody here?
A runaway from the vault.
Marcin Harcik, thin and not tall.
That maybe the one drowning in the river.
This was after the mass...
I killed a bear just with a knife.
Maybe with a wooden spoon?
And you, Casimirus, wouldn't
kill even a hare like this.
Prince, this is...
Do you want to try?
Sure.
Unless you're afraid.
Casimirus!
Just don't cry like a woman.
Let's see who's going to cry.
Yes, he's strong... You
need to find a way...
My sister's crying all the time.
Do you know that?
Say what you know!