Who's out there?
I'm here to speak to princess Aldona.
That is, Anna...
Casimirus's wife...
Prince Casimirus's?
Yes, the prince's...
You should rest, my lady...
I'll be watching....
I'll stay, father...
I believe the king can feel my presence.
My lady, you decide whether to wake princess Anna
I'd rather not be responsible for this.
And Poles are said to be so brave...
Yes, my lady...
Have you copied it?
Read the gospel...
to our son.
Take it easy. We'll pray for him.
Prayer is good
But allies, even better
They're on the way. The letters have been sent.
If I gave him a duchy...
He could rule peacefully....
and have a peaceful life.
But you've always wanted Casimirus to become the king.
Yes...
But the Polish crown...
is so heavy...
If not him, then who?
Crown is not a choice, it's a vocation, the heritage of blood...
He's got allies... sister, the queen of Hungary.
and Lithuanians, Anna's family...
It's a great force...
Few would dare challenge him...
But, Vladislav of Leczyca and Przemysl of Sieradz...
This is your family, your relatives...
I'm their direct paternal uncle...
but they've never accepted that
I became the king.
and, moreover
Casimirus is younger than them.
And the Czechs?
The Czechs? Jan is ready to ally with
the Brandenburg, the Teutonic Knights...
and then, he'll be on his own...
Who'll be with him?
I...
I'll be with him as I've always been with you...
Vladislav?
/murmuring/
Father?
He may be gone before night...
Speak! What did my brother say?
Relax. He's on the way.
I knew he'll come.
He should be here around tomorrow noon.
He sent me forward to let you know,
He'll be waiting in the Miechow Forest.
But how will I get there?
It's Lent. You can't ride a horse...
Do even horses fast in Poland?
Strange customs...
That's the way it is, so don't count on a rich breakfast...
Egle, give me some advice...
We'll come up with something tomorrow...
Algirdas is near, that's what counts.
Still, you'll have to explain his presence to your husband.
Prince Algirdas told me to say he sent me here to cheer you up.
And so that your daughters learn how to play the tarkas.
/Lithuanian/ Prince?
/Lithuanian/ - It's early.
- We're moving out.
/Lithuanian/ - Vladislav of Leczyca sleeps upstairs.
- The Hunchback?
/Lithuanian/ I want to avoid him.
/Lithuanian/ This is the king's nephew.
/Lithuanian/ He hates the Teutonic knights.
/Lithuanian/ Our ally.
/Lithuanian/ Ally?
/Lithuanian/ So, why is she sneaking to Krakow?
/Lithuanian/ He's got his right to the crown.
/Lithuanian/ And this is why we have to be at the Wawel Castle first.
I need boiling water.
Make a fire, woman.
Again, only bread and beer?
It's Lent. You forgot?...
Is it the king's breakfast?
Jesus was fasting for 40 days.
In the desert.
How can the king be healthy if all he eats is unhealthy.
Salvation of the soul. That's what matters.
- Right, Christian?
- We add some cheese.
Put it back. Today's Friday.
I said, only bread and beer!
So, at least, let my lady have a piece of cheese...
Is she pregnant?
No.
In this case she should fast. Like everyone.
How can she be pregnant if she's always fasting?
Vytautas?
This is Vytautas, my countryman. He brings goods from Lithuania.
Good day, my lord. I have the best goods. A royal feast, straight from Lithuania.
Show the goods to the lord!
Are we waiting for his highness?
Is he ill?
Owing to your prayers, he's in perfect health.
Where's your wife?
It's Lent. We don't sleep together, so I don't know where she is.
She should have heard the bells, though.
Lady, they're going to look for you.
Bishop Grot himself will hold the morning mass.
Bishop Grot? I can't miss the mass then.
Egle, you'll be serving the new princess Anna.
- My lady...
- Take off the cape. Quickly!
You'll be pretending our lady, you fool!
I'm going with you.
I'll take care myself, without a minstrel.
I was to watch you. You won't go without me.
And who's that?
An artist, my lady.
What if we're caught?
Nobody's going to know.
The queen will recognize me and give to the executioner.
You'll sit at the back.
You'll have a coat, pray and keep your head down,
and the veil will do the rest.
You only need to walk like a real queen,
and not sneak like a maidservant.
Enough talking, let's go.
My lady...
I'll do as you ordered, my lady.
Saddle the horse!
I'm going with the chatelaine to help the poor.
/praying in Latin/
Mom?
My lady, you can't leave the town.
Who said so?
It's dangerous. The guards will stop you.
Oh bright lady!
Help!
It's a conman!
Catch him!
Halt!
Follow me!
Stop!
Wife, come with me!
What does it mean?
Where is she? Speak immediately!
- I can't
- Speak before I get angry!
I swore to my lady.
Aren't you ashamed of your lies? Do you know it's a sin?
My wife's committing adultery and you keep quiet?
It's not adultery, I swear, she's loyal to you.
So, who is she meeting in secret?
Her brother.
Where?
Where? Speak!
The Miechow Forest. That's all I know, I swear.
What's going on?
You're going with me!
/Lithuanian/ Good day, my queen!
I'm not a queen.
/Lithuanian/ You'll be one soon, my darling.
/Lithuanian/ I wasn't sure it's you. You look stronger.
What does it mean, my lady?
Who's that man?
That's my brother, Algirdas, don't you recognize?
Put back your swords, as his hand is faster than his tongue.
/Lithuanian/ Should I kill them?
/Lithuanian/ Algirdas. This is my husband, Casimirus, and his knight, Jasko of Melszyn.
Were you running away to your brother?
I wasn't running away, but going out to greet him.
Galloping...
I'd expect anyone but you, my husband...
You neglect your wife....
Did she complain?
She didn't have to...
Everyone can see it...
Stop it. For my sister it may be somebody important.
You betrayed our lady.
If Casimirus catches them, he'll kill her. It'll be your fault.
They'll expel you from the court. Didn't you like it here?
I can't lie! It's a sin.
I have to speak with the prince urgently.
He went somewhere with Jasko. Don't you know?
I thought you're his most trusted man.
If I were him, I wouldn't trust anybody more than you.
I went to Sieradz and Leczyca.
Did you talk to Valdislav and Przemyslav?
Yes
Both are very concerned about your illness, my lord.
Maybe a bit too much.
As if they had made an agreement.
There are many troops on the roads.
And Teutonic knights?
They respect the peace and observe the truce.
Probably tired of winter.
But the prince of Leczyca is gathering knights.
He wants to attack the Order
to break the truce.
You should rest, my lord.
There's no time left. Give me the chest.
Knight!
Niemierza of Golcza
You've served my faithfully.
Take this ring.
Don't make him tired. Go now!
It's an honour
to serve the king.
I don't need rewards.
Take it, boy.
Go now, go!
Algirdas, the Lithuanian prince, princess Anna's brother, has come to Krakow.
Without our invitation...
Where's Anna?
Did she know of his coming?
She even went out to greet him.
Without our permission...
Did she take my carriage?
Horseback.
A savage.
So many years with us...
and still a pagan.
What are your orders, my lady?
Is your father in town or at the castle?
He's awaiting a call. He's been trying to see the king.
Send out for him.
I'll go myself.
No, you can't. You have to be at the castle when Algirdas is here.
I want to know what he and Anna are scheming.
Put these on this side.
At the beginning.
Bring it back to the storage.
It's Lent!
The Lithuanian prince arrived. The princess's brother. He doesn't fast.
This is why we serve fish, groats dumplings and vegetable stew.
Lent, but the royal way.
It's impolite to make the guest starve.
It's impolite to ignore the host's customs.
Here's miss Pelka...
She'll explain it to you...
what and how it should be.
You should return to Lithuania with your people.
Mother, you're speaking of my wife.
But this wife of yours is scheming against us with her brother.
I should send you back.
Lady, you have no right. I didn't betray my husband even in my thoughts.
How do you behave?
You ride a horse, go alone outside the castle.
- You don't pray
- Mother!
You need to deserve to wear the queen's crown.
Send for Spytek...
and the archdeacon of Jaroslav
I want to talk to them...
My lady, let me still be your knight...
Never!
You brought me so much embarrassment!
Look!
I can't talk!
But I can show how the king rewarded me. I had to leave because of his orders.
I'm not worthy of you.
I betrayed my lady.
What are you talking about, Cudka?
If only I could get my father's advice...
- He's left!
- He's gone on a secret mission!
Where?
I can't say, but he'll return.
You can be certain.
We need to talk.
Don't be afraid!
We're not angry with you, are we, my wife?
I want to look like a king.
Maybe it's too early to rise from your bed?
Rather too late.
Tell them to bring the broth.
And something fat.
But it's Lent.
This Lithuanian cook must have something in her stock.
Lent is needed for salvation of the soul, but that's not all.
I don't trust anybody. What if they poison you?
Who are you afraid of?
Everybody.
I'm not going anywhere.
So, why did you summon me?
You want help? Go to Lithuania with me.
No, Algirdas.
You have to go. The queen suspects you and I are scheming.
The old woman can't do anything.
She can.
She can have my marriage invalidated. I didn't think of it.
Your Casimirus is chasing after maidservants all the time.
Stop it.
He's my husband and the future king.
The old hag won't let you become the queen.
I'll take care of her.
Aldona
Prince Vladislav of Leczyca is near Krakow.
Prince of Sieradz will be here soon.
Jan of Bohemia will follow them.
Hungary.
They'll reach an agreement and there will be war.
They'll won't defeat Casimirus.
So, the cousins are there for a surprise.
When I tell them my will straight in their faces.
Casimirus must be the king.
They won't deprive him of the throne.
Do you believe in him so much?
I'm telling you he'll lose the crown.
The it will be too late to run. Come with me today.
No.
You go.
Go and tell that the old king is dying.
I have to stay here.
You summoned me and you're throwing me away.
Not throwing but asking.
I saw what you're wearing on your neck.
You haven't forgotten Lithuania...
and him...
Go now.
You may die here with Casimirus
They won't spare the girls either.
Here, either war or death is awaiting you...
...or the crown of the queen of Poland.