Is it your first time at Wawel?
/German/ Careful!
At last!
Difficult road!
Crowded! Had to wait!
For the last moment...
What's written here?
I see Casimirus, but here...
De... gra...
Dei gratia
Dei gratia - God's mercy, my son!
- I didn't look straight! - Not straight!
Give me a bowl and wax.
Beautiful...
Pity they don't make such in Krakow.
Don't take our jobs away!
Is Elizabeth here?
Tell me, mum. Nobody wants
to tell me anything.
Easy, Kunegunda.
Tell me!
No, I don't want!
You have to drink this medicine.
You've got fever.
Mum!
See? I'm drinking and I'm fine.
These are good herbs,
from Tyniec monastery.
You did it for me...
Drink!
Mum!
They're not so bitter.
Will you stay with me?
- Yes. - You will.
Lady! Queen Elizabeth has arrived.
She's come. At last!
We were worried, sister.
I sent another knight!
Mum prayed so much with a rosary
that she'll go straight to heaven!
The medics didn't allow me to go.
Then snow fell and Charles
didn't let me go.
And I didn't let Pelka go back.
I wanted to get to know everything myself.
He told me about you, the war
with the Teutonic Order,
about his daughter you took care of here.
Is Yolanta's mother dead for a long time?
The girl can hardly remember her.
Are you sure she's my child?
I wouldn't have sent her to you.
Why doesn't she speak?
She's not a mute. It's
simply her experiences.
I'm sorry, brother. I didn't
expect they would follow her here.
God, if something happened to you...
So, from the beginning I was their target.
I should have let you know.
Hadn't it been for Algirdas,
my daughter could be dead.
Where are the traitors?
We've got to sentence them.
In the vault.
We'll take care if it after the funeral.
No Hungarian can endanger the
life of the Polish king.
People need to know we won't spare...
The mass is coming soon!
Let's wait with it.
You need to act fast, trust me.
It's always safer this way.
You shouldn't delay the punishment.
Elizabeth!
At last!
At last we're all together.
How is Elizabeth dressed?
Is she wearing black or more fancy?
Your sister's asking about you, duchess!
Nobody's asking about
me and nobody needs me.
They should have poisoned me.
Don't say that, duchess.
Casimirus on the throne,
Elizabeth on the throne...
I'm only a duke's wife.
We were brought up together.
Elizabeth will start with
her paternalistic tone...
How I dislike it...
Little sister!
Your highness!
How are you?
Mum said you're sick.
Elizabeth...
Charles is ready to send his knights
if anyone defies our father's will.
It's good you're here.
You don't even know what's going on here.
You'll tell me everything.
My Kunegunda.
It's good you came.
Spytek!
At last, I'm at home!
Talk to your knight!
I'll be there soon!
Cudka!
It's for you!
Straight from Visegrad.
Try it on!
They say they're most
fashionable in Europe now.
But...
I can't take it.
It's good you're close to Casimirus.
He needs you very much, Spytek.
And your Jasko's become a knight!
I promised the king, and you
know I love him as my own son.
How is he doing?
I remember Father worried about him.
We both know his character...
He was very touched by the king's death.
But I hope he learnt from this situation
and he's recovering now, he'll be fine.
Can I help?
Don't hide anything from her, Spytek!
Tell her what Anna is doing.
Her maid refused baptism.
She does sorcery at the castle.
And Algirdas...
By the way, didn't your son
want the crown for himself?
Or so I heard.
For God's sake, Kunegunda, I don't
know why you persuaded him to do this.
Be careful! Here walls have ears.
Nobody will forgive and forget anything.
I won't forget what Casimirus
did at your court.
Calm down. We came here to
support him, not attack.
That's true, duchess.
We promised the king loyalty.
So, Spytek. Tell us what people
say of the Hungarian conspiracy.
What are you talking about, Kunegunda?
Didn't you know? Really?
Didn't you know those people
planned to kill Casimirus?
Enough, I won't let anybody offend me.
Elizabeth, Casimirus is waiting
for you in the chancery, hurry!
We're starting soon.
Has something happened?
Did you have an argument?
No, everything's fine, mum.
Pray together, Kunegunda
needs this very much.
Maybe grace of wisdom will fall upon her.
I don't want this dress.
A poor relative.
Have you seen how beautiful
Elizabeth's dress is?
So much embroidery and gold!
Do you think it makes her happier?
You've got one jewel more than her.
You've got a good heart.
Nothing else matters.
Now I'll be haunted by
three Casimirus's women:
Mother, sister Crazy and sister Queen.
And I'm all alone.
You're not alone. You've got Casimirus.
And that's a lot!
You should be happy because
he always stands by you.
Bring them in!
The sentence is to be read in
Visegrad during every mass.
You'll have it sent as soon
as we put our seals down.
Queen!
Laslo?
Istvan?
After so many years of
service at our court?
Lady, today is the king's funeral.
Pardon them.
We don't want pardon but Casimirus's death.
Off with their heads.
- This is my will. - No.
Hold it.
Beautiful! I'll do it the Lithuanian way.
We don't serve it this way.
What will you treat Elizabeth's court with?
You've seen how many have come.
It's Lent, not a binge.
I'll do it really well.
You won't be embarrassed.
I'll use horse radish
leaves and cure it first...
I said!
You won't do it.
Everything's ready. The oven's hot.
Yes. The oven's hot. We're by the oven
and there's the king's funeral there.
I served Vladislav for so many years,
and now I can't even see him off.
So, go!
He was important to you. I will manage.
We'll prepare everything as it should be.
No fish, no Lithuanian food, as you wish.
- Such an important event! - Go!
I'll promise I'll listen to the cook.
So, do it.
So, do it, do it the way you want.
Let them see how great
Lithuanian dishes are.
So, go now.
I'm going.
Do you prefer death to pardon?
You don't deserve death.
Death would be pardon.
Casimirus, the bells are tolling.
You should hang, murderer.
For Clara.
For Ferdinand.
- They will be aven... - Silence!
I sentence you to torture.
Chancellor, make sure it happens.
They're to suffer till they beg for death.
Take them!
Send it to Visegrad as soon as possible.
My husband needs to know the
Zachs' case is finally over.
You know what to do!
Yes, I'm to follow the knight.
Do you know which one?
This is knight Pelka.
He's putting on the king
Vladislav's armour.
Father, what honour...
There's no more honourable knight among us.
This is the king's cape.
Pelka, I'm happy it's you.
The king admired you very much.
Where's your husband?
You can't go without him.
Accept my gratitude.
I heard that but for you
the princesses could be dead.
I saved my sister's daughters,
they're half Lithuanians. Accept the fact.
Is your brother always so cheeky?
He's so gentle with you
that I can't recognize him.
Where's Yolanta?
Where you sent her, with our daughters.
She was in danger. She's
Casimirus's child, our blood.
Let's go.
The first one's wearing the king's cape.
The one in black is death.
Death? It's a knight!
That means the king is dead.
/praying in Latin/
God, have mercy on my lord's soul.
Elizabeth...
Please, sit next to me.
I want to talk to Anna.
Kunegunda...
Thank you, I'll be here, on the other side.
Sit next to me.
Do you mind?
It's great honour.
Ask my cook for the wine I brought.
Elizabeth, it's Lent.
Even the pope in Avignon
drinks wine in Lent.
Don't worry, I didn't bring anything
that would break your rules.
Queen, am I to pour?
Mother, please agree.
It's our best Cerman wine.
All right, but just for trying.
Let's keep this wine for
Casimirus's coronation.
Forgive us.
Casimirus, I need you for a moment.
The sentence was announced.
You know I can't do anything for you.
Why did you call me?
You do it for us. Yes, you!
- Kill king Casimirus! - You're insane!
Avenge your countrymen. There
won't be a better opportunity.
Did he suffer?
More because of the loss of
Kuyavia than the illness.
You knew him.
You know what mattered to him.
What did he say? Did he mention me?
Yes, he asked to say goodbye to you.
He said how he was proud of you,
how well you rule.
What did he really tell you?
Not to trust the Teutonic
knights and recapture Kuyavia.
Remember you can count on us.
Charles will send troops if
anyone disturbs the coronation.
I hope it won't happen.