At this time? What can be so urgent?
Lady, archdeacon Jaroslav.
Your majesty.
I know the reason why
Anna can't be crowned.
Adultery.
What are these suspicions based on?
I'm not suspecting. I know.
Your majesty.
Stanislava, call Casimirus in.
He has to know.
The king is praying with Elias before
the coronation. Is it necessary?
It's necessary.
I must see Aldona one more time. Help me!
How did you get in here?
I must say something very
important to Aldona.
Anna!
King Casimirus's wife, who
will be crowned today.
Have you lost your mind?
I beg you.
It's a matter of life and death.
Mother, mind your words, please!
And with whom?
A common knight, and a pagan!
Lady, maybe this needs to be verified?
I'm doing this!
- I'm verifying! - No, it's crazy...
Summon Algirdas and Kestutis. It's
impossible the brothers don't know about it.
Everybody has to make an oath.
Anna and chambermaids. Everybody!
Here! Now!
Today is the coronation. The kingdom's
festival... Let's not ruin it.
- It can do harm.
- She's not faithful to my son.
- Are you sure, lady? - I've got a witness.
Lady, prince Algirdas and prince Kestutis.
Who needs help?
My son. Your sister has betrayed him.
We won't let anybody offend her.
Casimirus I didn't expect this.
I trust my wife.
Prince, are you ready to swear
on what's dearest to you,
that you know nothing of
your sister's affair?
I vouch for her virtue with my honour.
And do you vouch too, prince?
Don't accuse me, please.
Neither me, nor my sister.
She's faithful to her husband.
That means the case is closed.
It should be enough for you, Mother.
Don't walk away, please.
Helen. When Anna comes, you'll tell
us what you saw, under the oath.
Let everybody hear the truth.
Tell me what's this about.
You know something. You won't cheat me.
- Did Aldona betray Casimirus? - No!
- So, who are they talking about?
- Arunas, your knight.
Where is he? Where's Aldona?
You must come with me. That's
queen Jadwiga's order.
We're to swear Anna never
betrayed Casimirus...
It's obvious.
And that she was alone
at night recently.
Swear on the relics of St.
Jadwiga of Silesia.
How can I swear if I don't know?
I was by my father's bed.
But you've been with her every
day for last eight years.
This will decide Anna's
coronation, maybe even her life.
Am I to lie?
You're to help her.
This is what service is about.
Kneel.
Cross yourselves.
What are they doing?
They're praying over chrism.
It's a special kind of oil
with which your father will be
anointed at the coronation.
The king's authority comes from God.
The archbishop confirms it with this sign.
It's as if your father was
no longer just a human.
Is our mother going to be anointed too?
Of course, she's king's wife.
Did Grandma agree?
Grandma loves all your family.
Your mother too.
Queen Jadwiga shouldn't
agree to Anna's coronation.
The king decides everything.
Something happened?
No, everything's fine.
Pray for your parents.
Why didn't you tell me?
He didn't want to go.
I forced him.
You took him yourself.
If I had known, I wouldn't
have taken him to Krakow.
Aldona chose Casimirus,
what do you want from me?
What if she runs away with him?
She's responsible. I trust her, don't you?
I do, too.
But there's darkness in her heart.
The whole alliance may break
apart because of one knight.
We've got to find him.
Lady, I insist.
I didn't do anything improper.
Give me the rings.
The queen summons you.
You can go Stanislava.
I'll come when I'm ready.
What's going on with you?
How can I swear if I don't know?
I wasn't there.
They'll tell me to swear on
the relics of St. Jadwiga...
- Tell the truth! - So, we must know it.
I can lie for you, but I
want to know how it was.
I went to see Arunas.
- Alone? - Yes!
But I didn't betray my husband!
A conversation is not adultery.
A conversation and feelings can be a sin.
Do you think so?
Queen Jadwiga thinks so,
and she will judge you.
Thought, words and desires can be a sin,
but she doesn't care of
your salvation but power.
I'll be delighted to say I was there.
She's hurt you so much for all these years,
and I won't let her win.
Cudka, send for brother Wojciech. If there's to
be a trial, there should be someone just there.
- If she really... - Come on!
The words of the oath
have to be written down.
Helen, you've got to be here. All the time.
I'll never leave you.
And I'll always love you.
But you won't see me anymore.
Let's get it over with.
What are you accusing me of, Mother?
I'm not your mother.
Husband, if you want, I'll swear.
And so will my maids.
Egle can't swear on relics.
Cudka can.
Cudka cared of her wounded
father at that time, didn't she?
Anna couldn't have done anything improper.
Can you prove it?
Will you swear?
/Lithuanian/ Where's Arunas?
Was he with you all night?
/Lithuanian/ When did
you see him last time?
/Lithuanian/ At dusk. He said he was
told to visit Krakow, so he went.
Arunas had better not be found.
Just a suspicion of an affair
with the queen means death.
I had better not find him.
Praised be Jesus Christ.
For ever and ever.
Brother Wojciech, come over here, please.
Cudka, swear that
Anna, daughter of Giediminas,
the wife of my son Casimirus
is faithful to him.
Remember that perjury is a sin.
Forgive lady, forgive Anna, I can't.
I assure you, Casimirus, I'm innocent.
I swear I didn't betray you.
Thank you wife, I believe you.
Helena, come.
It's your turn now.
I swear last night I saw
Anna, daughter of Giediminas,
the wife of Casimirus
meeting secretly a Lithuanian knight.
She's lying.
Is it true?
I must see the abbot.
A Lithuanian?
A knight. Please.
I didn't betray you and I'm
not afraid of the truth.
Yes, I spoke to a Lithuanian knight.
But I didn't offend against the duties
of wife and mother with any deed.
Why Anna?
I asked him to never come
to Wawel, and that's all.
Why did you meet him secretly?
And who would let us talk freely?
Knight Arunas didn't come here out of
his volition. He was ordered to come.
Like I was ordered to
come here the other day.
I always obeyed my father.
I never betrayed the king and I
have nothing to blame myself for.
But Helena saw you together.
The clouds covered the moon, and..
But, yes... I saw them as
if in each other's arms.
Helen, why are you lying?
I don't want to see the
one who's lying anymore.
He wants to see you.
Probably from Lithuania.
You wanted to talk to the abbot.
Bring me to him, sire.
It's me.
How can I help?
I'd like to join your order.
Have you suddenly felt a calling or
you're running away from somebody?
I want to sacrifice my life to God.
Follow me, knight.
Say what you know.
I saw. I prefer not to
have seen it, but I did.
Helen, are you sure of what you saw?
- We're sometimes misled by our senses.
- Speak!
Go on, what did you see?
I didn't see!
Did you lie?
I misled you, queen. I'm sorry.
They talked in the moon light.
This man reached out his hand.
But Anna withdrew...
I didn't tell you this. I'm sorry.
You lied to me.
My husband. I've never been with
another man since we're together.
I love you and I'll support you.
Son...
Do you believe her?
Are you sure you're ready
for such life, knight?
I don't have needs.
We live like this. Here in Tyniec,
in Swiety Krzyz, in Monte Cassino.
And we keep repeating the same rule.
Teach me, sire.
Whoever you are, and you
eschew your desires,
willing to serve Jesus Christ,
you put on a mighty and holy armour...
of obedience.
I know how to be obedient.
Do you know how to stay silent?
Our rule says even good
or holy conversations
should be allowed only
rarely to advanced learners.
The Scripture says: Sin is not
ended by multiplying words.
Life and death are under
the tongue's control.
I'll stay silent.
My name's Arunas. The one who
gets everything his way.
You'll have to adopt a
different, conventual one.
I request a baptism.
Did you commit a crime?
I love a woman who will never be mine.
I want to give this love to your god.
You fool.
You'll tell Him about yourself.
I only need to know who this woman is.
Virgin, Mother of God, God-famed Mary!
Ask Thy Son, our Lord, God-named Mary,
To have mercy upon us
and hand it over to us!
Kyrie eleison!
/praying in Latin/
Listen to the prayer we say,
For what we ask, give us today:
Life on earth free of vice;
After life: paradise!
Kyrie eleison!
May everyone be subject to authority
ruling over the others.
There is no authority
that doesn't come from God.
And those that exist
are constituted by God.
Let us walk honestly, as in the day
not in rioting and drunkenness,
not in chambering and wantonness,
not in strife and envying.
But put ye on the Lord Jesus Christ,
and make not provision for the flesh,
to fulfill the lusts thereof.
/praying in Latin/