Stanislava, where's my mother?
She prayed whole night
by the king's coffin.
Mother!
Whose child is this?
/singing in Latin/
Mother, we have more important
issues to discuss now.
But it's important too.
Very important.
So, answer me.
Father just died and you
care of some stranger child.
Stranger?
She looks like yours.
I'm not going to explain.
Either to you or anybody.
An illegitimate child.
Don't we have enough problems
because your marriage with a pagan?
What if it reaches the pope?
I believe you'll take care
so that it doesn't happen.
How much time has passed since
your return from Hungary?
You said everything was fixed,
and there will be no trace
of your adventure with this girl anymore.
There is no trace.
Since Clara's father raised his
sword against the king and queen
the court sentenced their
whole family to death.
So, it's not Clara Zach's child?
I swear it's not.
Elizabeth swore none of them survived.
Wait.
What are we to do with her?
This is king Vladislav.
The father of our lord, Casimirus.
He was a good king.
And a good father.
Can you hear me?
We have to be good to prince Casimirus.
He's very sad now.
/whispering/
Yolanta, can you speak?
You know the prayer for the dead?
You speak!
This is the seal of Elizabeth, your sister.
It's clearly written -
protect the child of
Casimirus, the king of Poland.
But it doesn't have to be my daughter.
She'll be safe in a monastery.
Yolanta, she has my mother's name.
For the memory of your dead father,
tell the truth.
There was another woman...
in Visegrad, at Charles's court.
In that case,
you can't get rid of this child,
in whose veins our blood flows.
We need to keep her.
I won't do it to Anna.
Do you care of Anna now?
You should have thought about it then.
Besides, if she were a good wife...
She is! a good wife.
So, she will understand.
This child may be an obstacle
to Casimirus's coronation.
The pope agreed for it long ago.
But Casimirus does
everything against himself.
First, marriage with a pagan,
trouble at Hungarian court,
murder in Koscian,
war with the Teutonic Order...
Not enough? And now this?
Casimirus is not ready
to sit on the throne.
On the contrary, he's ready,
and he'll be the king.
And we have to support him.
We promised that to his father.
He's the laughing stock of Europe.
He fled the battlefield at Plowce.
The Teutonic knights
spread the news already.
And he behaves like a pagan.
And do you, excellency,
always behave like a bishop?
Brave!
He must have already snitched to the pope.
What about the girl?
It would be best to send
her back to the monastery.
But she may be in danger.
If this is the king's daughter,
we must protect her.
The court will boil over with gossip.
Only for a while...
Then they'll soon find another topic.
And what about the bishop?
How the please the "conscience" of Krakow?
I'll ask him to crown
Casimirus together with me.
He likes being important.
And what about Ann?
You know that she can get angry.
It's time she had her chaplain.
Someone who'll teach her how to forgive.
This way.
To the inn.
This is a longer route.
You said we were to go as fast as possible.
It's not good Anna was left there alone...
I have a bad premonition.
You want to go back?
How many times did Aldona tell
you they don't want us there?
That because of us there
may be no coronation.
But, since she called for my help,
maybe I should stay?
I'll ask gods.
Honey?
It's for the girls.
Lent hasn't ended yet.
They're Christians too.
And they'll think God loves them.
So, can I bring it to them?
Add the third one.
So, it's true.
What's true?
That Casimirus fasts.
But only under his mother's eyes.
Stop it! Bring it!
And be reasonable with the honey.
Egle, why doesn't Yolanta speak?
Maybe she can't.
But Cudka said Yolanta knows prayers.
Maybe she doesn't want to speak.
Sometimes when one has
some terrible experience
words are not enough...
I'll tell you a legend of a good
goddess, the queen of snakes
Grandma doesn't allow us to
listen to legends of gods
So, I'll tell you about the
love of Milda and Ramois.
It's not a legend. We
call it an itolorauda.
Is it true?
Yes.
It begins in a Lithuanian forest.
Egle, the lady's calling you.
I'll take care of them.
Do you know a true story about love?
Pour.
No froth.
Pour more.
Still no froth.
A bad omen.
Beer.
/speaking Hungarian/
Hungarians.
Give us more beer.
I can't keep quiet because
I'm not like them.
And I won't pretend everything's all right.
So talk to him?
Now? When he's taking over the kingdom?
Praised be Jesus Christ.
I'm brother Wojciech of Dominican Order.
And I'm a cursed Lithuanian.
That's what your brethren say about me.
Shall we pray?
You in Lithuanian, I in Polish.
In Lithuanian? Your god can
understand only Latin.
You speak to him with your own words.
He will understand for sure.
Tell him everything you fear.
I don't fear. I'm mad.
I'll pray for you, then.
All you can do is to scare people
with hell and take their joy away.
Tell all your complaints to God,
who died on the cross for us.
He'll help you for sure.
/speaking Hungarian/
Edmundas, you've been to Hungary.
Can you understand what they say?
The bearded one mentioned Casimirus.
We can cast dice.
As you wish.
All omens are bad.
/speaking Hungarian/
They said something about Casimirus
but I didn't hear everything.
They say they're going to
stay till the very end.
As if they waited for the king's funeral.
They came from Visegrad
and have some important
matters to take care of.
I think they mentioned vengeance.
Nothing more?
There was a bad omen.
I have to go back.
You stay here and watch them.
Beer.
Quickly.
/Hungarian/
Jesus Christ!
You promised you wouldn't drink.
The city is mourning. I'm
crying after the dead king.
And you're drinking...
Have you got no shame?
I'm drinking because...
Because?!
I did a terrible thing.
Of course, terrible.
I had to close the stall myself.
If not Joseph, the potter, I'd
have to carry everything myself.
Shame! I have a husband and
strangers have to help me.
I'll do penance...
May God forgive my sins...
Anna, they're waiting for me...
Egle said it's urgent.
You must know what I want to talk about.
This girl's name is the same
as your pious grandma's.
- Anna, please... - Say!
Were you unfaithful to me?
Be frank with me!
Yes, there was another woman.
Anna, I'm sorry.
I can't reverse it, but
you're the queen now.
I promise you...
I trusted you...
I've always been faithful and loyal to you.
You could trust me too.
I'm not going to kneel, but I beg you.
As your husband, as the
king, as Vladislav's son...
He liked you so much.
I beg you. For his memory.
Help me.
I beg you.
My granddad kept telling my father
"Don't look back if you want
to build a strong state".
The spirits will involve
you in their games.
The spirits...
For now, there are so many people
that there's no room for any spirit.
And everyone wants to gain
something from my father's death.
Focus on the crown, not
the coffin, Casimirus.
You'll have to take care of
the kingdom, not mourning.
You can leave the latter to your mother.
She's always mourning.
Will you let Yolanta stay?
I beg you.
I can't send her away
now, it's too dangerous.
You have to promise me something.
When you become king, you'll guarantee the
right to the throne to our daughters.
Anna, you know I can't do it. In Poland
only sons can inherit the throne.
Now, you will be the king.
And you can change it.
My lord, forgive me, but
I have to say this...
It hasn't been possible to tell
you this, but I want you to know
I feel very sorry for king Vladislav...
I loved him like my father.
I commiserate with you.
Thank you.
Pray for him.
I pray for him every day.
I know it's hard to lose the father but
your highness has still got
his mother, and wife...
You summoned me, sire...
You'll go to Visegrad to inform
my sister of our father's death.
But Pelka has already gone there...
Yes, but he's not returned
and Elizabeth hasn't come.
Something bad must have happened.
Does Cudka know?
You'll take the best horse.
Tell the treasurer to give
you as much as you need.
I'll take her of her.
Quick!
Look! He lost his mind
because of this beer...
Where did he get the money for drinking?
Didn't he steal from you?
I've lived too long with him
to keep money in sight.
I know how to hide it from him.
He can hide it from you too...
He mentioned 30 pieces of silver...
Holy Mary!
This is money from the devil!
Easy, woman...
He must have stolen it.
Take it.
The king's dead.
Hard times are coming.
Martin, what have you done?
It's obvious we all feel sorry
for the dead king Vladislav.
When they bring the coffin to the
church, we'll go to the ceremony.
But now, guests are coming
to the Wawel Castle.
Where's the Lithuanian?
She should hear it too.
The canon and the bishop
will hold the ceremony,
and when they pray long,
they can eat a lot.
You, cup-bearer, prepare more mead and beer
The life of our future king depends
on what we put on the table.
And remember, I always tell you
There will be strangers in the castle
And it's always dangerous
We have to be careful, very careful
Did you hear?
And cook only food for fasting?
Exactly!
Get down to work.
Do you want to tell me something?
No, I'm only cleaning.
So, what are you waiting for?
Knead the dough.
I'm on it!
I'd like to cut rumours and speculation.
The girl named Jolanta
will stay at the court.
My mother and I decided
we're not sending her away.
Wouldn't she be better
off in the monastery?
She's still a child...
If she chooses monastery in the
future, I won't stop her...
Now, she stays here.
So, this topic's finished.
Now, I'd like you to be frank with me.
You know you can always count on us.
So, let's try to clarify our situation now.
Are you ready for it?
I prefer the worst truth
than courtly make-up.
Spytek, how about the
treasury, who can I count on
and what's the gravest danger now?
The truth is... treasury is almost empty.
We can't afford any war.
When does the truce with
the Teutonic Order expire?
By Pentecost.
These are the terms of the
truce with the Order.
Pope's consent to the marriage with Anna.
Lithuania is your strong
ally, remember, Casimirus.
Can we count on them? Trust them?
I hear all the time they're pagans,
that this alliance was a mistake...
But your daughters are half-Lithuanian
these are strong bonds.
Giediminas knows it too.
Guards!
Open!
Look, how much Father managed to achieve.
I want the subjects to
remember him for ever.
I'll order a tomb that
will survive all wars.
Great. But we have to wait with the
funeral and the coronation for Elizabeth.
I hope Niemierza will reach Hungary soon.
Remember, you can count only in
your sister and nobody else.
Father trusted Giediminas too.
Don't count on pagans.
Count only on Hungarians and on me.
I can forgive Casimirus this one time only.
But I won't let myself
be humiliated anymore.
Algirdas?
What are you doing here?
I came back to warn you.
Hungarians are scheming
against your husband.