Lady...
Let's keep this conversation between us.
Let's cancel today's council.
Let's eat a family lunch without politics.
But all the princes can't
wait to talk about it.
That's why I need your help.
I don't want to create an opportunity
for anybody to attack him
or question his position.
What kind of an idea is this?
He'll manage.
But these conflicts won't do any good.
Vladislav nominated
Casimirus for the throne.
You heard it.
Isn't it enough to make everybody shut up?
Let him defend his crown.
What if he doesn't convince them?
Then we'll invoke the dead king's will.
What if they mutiny?
New times are coming.
Now even women can inherit the crown.
Are you afraid of this, my lady?
My daughters disappointed me very much.
One stood against her brother
and the other didn't even come.
Queen Elizabeth will come for sure.
Elizabeth has always been your soft spot.
I am her godfather!
If your husband does what he
promised, you'll be fine.
My husband will never betray the king!
This has already happened. Now
he has to do what he promised.
Have mercy! Release the children!
Keep me, but let the kids go!
This doesn't depend on me.
Help! Help!
Enough!
Now, only your husband can save you.
/Hungarian/ At last! At
last I can hear crying.
/Hungarian/ This is all
king Casimirus's fault.
I have to come in!
Excuse me, lady, but the cook master
says he's got an important issue.
Excuse me, but it's very urgent.
Speak!
I'm afraid poison has been
brought into the castle.
Afraid? I don't understand.
Has it been brought in or not?
Excuse me, lady, but I can't be sure.
I appreciate your concern, but I
don't know what the issue is?
Who are you suspecting?
I'm not sure.
When you find the suspect, bring him to me.
Even the slightest betrayal
must be punished severely.
One more thing,
tell the table master and the
cup bearer to test every dish.
For everybody
We must be careful and very strict.
It will be enough.
As you wish, my lady.
Why was I so foolish to return here?
He must have gone to the queen.
They're going to torture me.
I don't understand why I
came here from Lituhuania
and can't get adjusted for so many years...
Don't report on me to the
queen, she hates Lithuanians
They'd better push me of the cliff or cut,
I don't want tortures...
- Say who brought the poison - Not me.
Don't you remember any
stranger in our kitchen?
There was one on the day the king died.
He helped carry bags with flour.
He said he was looking
for a job and for you.
I chased him away.
Do you remember how he looked?
Like a common man, not much
brain, even less shame...
Knead the dough.
And cook enough groats, so
it's enough for everybody.
Didn't you report on me to the queen?
If you had wanted to
poison the king's family,
you'd have done it long ago...
It will end badly.
It would be better if
Casimirus persuaded them
rather than ruled against them.
They should obey the king's will.
Soon, everybody will want
to have something to say.
And these rumours of
Hungarian conspirators.
This must end!
And my cook who sees poison everywhere.
The guards watch everything night and day.
That's not enough, castellan.
Find the culprits and give
them to the executioner.
Let people see we'll not spare anybody
the sooner it happens, the better.
But, my lady, we don't know
who the conspirators are...
So, have another criminal beheaded.
Make them fear
let anyone who stands up against
the king know the consequences.
Fear is the best guard.
If only my mother knew
that we do it during Lent
after Father's death...
If you didn't think of your
mother when you're with me
and think of me when
you're with your mother
all of us would be better off.
Oh, a crown again!
Divination is a sin!
Do you believe God looks into our bedroom
and sees these scattered wheat ears?
I don't know.
Ask Father Wojciech about it.
Do you know he's been here?
I'm the future king.
I know what my wife's doing.
But you don't know what she's going to do.
And I saw it...
I don't believe such sorcery.
I make decisions, do you understand?
Not blind fate...
Not my mother.
I!
Will you persuade your
mother to my coronation?
And will you have a new crown made for me?
But such one with many jewels and
so that I could dance in it?
Is Casimirus with his wife?
They're discussing matters of the kingdom.
- The guests are gathering for the council.
- No one can disturb them.
Superb embroidery...
As if the ornament flowed from
your fingers on the canvas...
This is for Niemierza of Golcza.
My knight.
Is he an envoy again?
I'm not allowed to discuss it.
I am.
I know where he went and what for.
Do you know anything about my father?
Don't worry. He's the bravest of knights.
He will return.
Everybody's waiting.
You could have knocked.
I'd have had to kill Cudka,
or tie her, at least.
Such guard would be useful
at the gates of Wawel.
Help Anna get dressed.
And you, sire?
I'm not going ot dress up.
Martin, you'd better go back.
Again, you're ducking out of work.
Come on, you're not working today either.
The axes are sharpened,
but the vaults are empty.
So help us carry bags.
We need to bring groats to Wawel.
More and more guests are
coming to the king's funeral.
Your woman's making money from
it, so what to worry about?
If only you knew...
Laudetur lesus Christus.
I'd better go.
I've got work to do.
My old woman's not a weakling, but still...
She won't carry everything
to Wawel by herself.
Why are you looking at them?
Martin, be careful.
You can't touch an envoy.
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
I won't sit at the table with them.
I don't trust strangers.
There are too many of them around.
Algirdas, they're not so dangerous.
I've got a bad premonition.
Who'd dare to use poison at the castle?
Everyone. I saw those
in the throne chamber.
One would be happy to pour
poison the the other's cup.
Send this beauty away, I advise you.
Cudka?
I brought her up.
This didn't make her uglier.
She's got her knight. Niemierza of Golcza.
This won't be an obstacle to your husband.
Send her to the old woman.
Keep Egle. You can trust her.
I can take care of myself.
I know. But send her away.
Are you out of mind?
Where have you been?
I checked if they're alive.
What are you looking for?
A proof that we're serious.
What do you want to do?
I'll pay a visit. In Wawel.
What beer to serve? Weaker or stronger?
Serve mead.
But we were to fast.
For me, only herbs. For the
guests, the best mead.
I want everyone to make a toast.
For the king.
Hurry!
Let's not delay it, gentlemen.
Say what's on your mind.
Casimirus, let me begin.
"The mighty will be mightily
tormented", says the Book of Wisdom.
God is the strictest evaluator of kings
but the book also says that
"Whoever seeks wisdom will
find her sitting at the door."
My lords, rise.
I want to make a toast.
Long live Casimirus, king of Poland.
I disagree!
I'm king Vladislav's grandson.
Why do we need a king?
Instead of coronation, let's
just partition the land,
like our great grandfather Boleslaw did.
We're all equal.
Quiet!
Let's hear what prince Bolko has to say.
What right do you have to undermine the
will of king Vladislav and the pope?
I'll accuse you of betrayal.
Do it.
Do it, mother.
Show how you love the family.
But remember, "the mighty
will be mightily tormented."
Don't invoke the Scripture in such anger.
My sister and I had to obey.
Marry whom you told us,
go where you sent us.
Elizabeth is a queen,
Casimirus will soon be king,
and I?
Have you ever thought about me?
Quiet.
Let him speak.
Look, is he to be the king? A mute?
Speak, son!
Where are the queen's herbs?
Over there!
Take it to the table, quickly!
Put it here.
That's him!
He was here with the millers
and tampered with the shelf!
That's him!
Are you sure?
I recognize him!
Guards!
You said you were looking
for a job, confess!
You're lying, woman!
Who would let him in the castle?
What's on?
I didn't want to kill the king.
Give it to me. I'll bring it.
Go back to the kitchen,
you're needed there.
I have to do it myself.
I'll bring it.
To the cup-bearer.
Of course.
Why is it so hot?
Do I work in the kitchen?
They asked, so I brought it.
A son or a grandson may be the king.
You fled at Plowce.
We don't want a coward as the king.
You have a big mouth and
only in Wawel, uncle.
But who could you stand
against in the field?
He's right!
Listen to him!
In my own castle... My nephew...
Wait them out, let them talk.
There's poison in the castle.
You know our achievements.
You know who fled from the battlefield.
Casimirus.
Who defeated the Czechs?
I.
I'm innocent. I brought spices.
A man came, paid, told me to bring it.
So I brought it.
Just a pouch. I didn't know it's poison.
Have mercy, castellan.
But later, I did penance.
Who gave you this? Or
you're going to the vault.
A stranger. I never saw him again.
What did he look like.
Hooded but not a monk.
Big, but not tall.
Strange because he paid in advance.
Where is it?
He drank it away.
To the vault.
I know where they meet.
I'll tell you everything.
They?
The hooded one and... Hungarians.
Hungarians?
Are you sure?
You can't mistake their language.
Why do we need the crown?
We have strong duchies.
We're good rulers, each on his own.
They caught the one who brought poison.
Go to the guards and learn who sent them.
I wanted...
What did you want?
Doesn't matter.
Tell me what's happening.
What are they saying?
Prince Bolko says he'll be a better king.
And what did Casimirus say?
Did he oppose him?
I saw how Casimirus looks at you.
Be careful.
We have peace with princes of Stettin.
We live on good terms
with the Wittelsbachs.
Brandenburg poses no danger to us.
Let's share.
It's easier to govern a duchy
than the whole kingdom.
Lower costs, so life is easier.
Enough.
We're not partitioning the kingdom.
The king's already up there,
he sacrificed his life to unite Poland,
and what did you sacrifice?
I'll never let you ruin it!
You want only the crown, don't you?
No, Bolko. I want time.
Here. I drank with them here.
You're lying?
Here, I swear.
Kill him on the spot.
Who was with them?
I said, Hungarians.
What did they look like?
Two young ones, one tall.
One young with a scar on his cheek.
Did he pay?
No, the hooded one.
I'll crush his skull!
Not here, my lord!
Yes, he'll tell you I'm innocent.
Do you know him?
Of course, everybody knows him.
The last time I saw him,
he drank with Hungarians.
They were very generous.
You'll hang. That's for sure.
It's not me. It's the hooded one.
He either threatens or
tempts with money. Devil!
Was there anybody hooded with them?
No, only he and the Hungarians.
What do I pay you for?
Go away!
You were not to come here.
I'm waiting for the bells tolling.
I did what you wanted. Free my children.
- You swore. - Of course.
Where are they?
With the Hungarians.
Do your job.
Come to the inn.
You'll get the reward...
and your family.
You know what to do next.
Close the gate. Don't let any stranger in.
Bring him to the vault.
Have the whole Wawel searched.
Sire, should we let those in?
Who are you?
An envoy from the Great Master
Lothar von Braunschweig.
Should we let the envoy in?
We can't separate, Przemysl,
because there will be war again.
And not only at the borders
but also between us.
There will be war in the family,
and people are tired with
war, they're afraid.
You're afraid.
You say partitions wer better.
Maybe then, but not today.
Today we're not a power state,
but we can be one tomorrow.
Charles Robert's building a strong Hungary.
Jan of Bohemia strengthened teh Czechs.
My father-in-law, Giediminas,
rules a great country.
Pagan!
And the Teutonic knights?
You'll never defeat them.
Let's share.
Let Casimirus speak!
My mother, queen of Poland is right.
"The mighty will be mightily tormented",
so before you say, "Let's
partition Poland",
think if your children will be free.
The Teutonic knights are only
waiting till Poland is weaker
We need to act united because
only then are we strong!
I was at the father's death.
I swore I'll recover Kuyavia,
and I'll keep my word.
He's dead.
Poison.
Treason at Wawel!