We have peace until next Pentecost.
The Great Master Lothar von Braunschweig
signed the truce on hitherto terms.
Didn't he try to force us to break
the alliance with Lithuania?
No, he didn't even mention it.
Your adamant stance when
negotiating with the envoy
must have been successful, sire.
I'm asking you for one thing
let's not forget Kuyavia.
I promised Father I'll recapture Kuyavia.
We don't forget it, lady.
Still, all of us agree that now
a war with the Order
would end in a disaster.
Not all of us.
Bishop?
Lady! You have a guest.
Is Algirdas already back?
He was to visit the salt mines.
Are you alone?
May I come in?
What are you hiding there?
Gingerbread?
May I try?
Really?
Can't you see I want to try them?
So good!
At Plowce, king Vladislav
led our knights to victory.
The Teutonic knights had to withdraw
and they failed to join with
John of Bohemia's forces.
Have you forgotten the reception
when you returned to Krakow?
No, I haven't.
So, why are you wasting a
chance for the final victory?
Why do you want to wait until the Teutonic
Order rebuilds it power and attacks us again?
I know, there's no money. I
hope it's only about this.
I hope if excellency wanted
accuse me of cowardice,
he'd be brave enough to
tell this face to face.
This is not an act of capitulation.
This is the proof of a new order.
I want less destruction
and more construction.
It's good in peaceful times.
Our times won't be peaceful when
our only tactics is the sword.
When troops move to and fro through
our lands and our houses burn.
In this way, the land
will never be prosperous.
It won't be a European
power like the others.
Sire, tell our knights about it.
If they have no real enemy, they'll
find one among themselves.
Enough! I'm expecting sound arguments.
Counselling the king is a vocation.
If someone doesn't understand this,
they don't deserve to be here.
Chancellor, issue the document.
My copy of the truce is to be ready for
the coronation, on St. Mark's day.
There aren't many people close
to you at the court, are there?
I've got daughters, Egle,
Cudka and Casimirus.
It's not easy to tell
your secrects to a man.
I'll hide it in case the queen came here.
You both still don't get on well, do you?
Yes, but I think it's my fault.
Have you already got a
dress for the coronation?
I don't know if I'll be crowned.
You've got to be prepared
for either situation.
And look good in either, for your subjects.
And look beautiful for your husband.
I've brought a few of my dresses.
You'll see what's hot in Europe.
We'll think of something.
I've brought a great tailor from Venice.
You should think of it too.
Don't expect your husband
to have this idea.
We'll meet as often as necessary
and solve the current problems.
We're at your order, sire.
And another thing...
I want to know what's going
on behind the castle walls.
Too often do we forget about our subjects.
Our world is the crown and the court,
but they've got other concerns.
The wealthy and the knights
will say they want to fight.
I'm not talking about knights.
I'm talking about simple folks.
I've been among them recently.
I heard their complaints.
Where? Here in Wawel?
No. At a roadside inn.
An inn? Son, that's not
a place for the king.
And where's his place if
nor among the subjects?
The council's meeting is over.
Thanks to everyone.
Please, ask Jasko not to leave
the king even for a moment
if my son wants to travel outside Krakow.
That's unheard of!
There won't be a better moment.
We've got a good position for attack.
We can always negotiate.
That's right. It would be a mistake
to miss such an opportunity.
But the king doesn't understand this.
He's too young and too inexperienced.
The knights will be happy to join.
The prince of Sieradz will join.
I talked to him. He'll join even today.
Excellent!
We'll go, but only with Casimirus.
You have to persuade him
to renounce the truce.
Because if we start without him,
we'll have new enemies - him and Hungary.
Show them to the tailor. Let her
make something similar for you.
All of them are beautiful.
Try on the one you like most.
It's this one.
ELizabeth, may I ask you a question?
When Casimirus stayed at your court...
did he take Clara by force?
You know him. Do you think
he'd be able to do it?
I think not.
So, why are you listetning to
rumours spread by his enemies?
Clara gave herself to him.
But it's true that Casimirus has
always been attracted by women.
I'm blaming myself I didn't watch him then.
Fate didn't favor us either.
At the begining... children,
one and then the other
and there was no room for tenderness.
The he went to you, and
this scandal erupted.
It's terrible to hear such
things of your own husband.
And he exposed me and
the children to risk...
Me too. I lost my fingers.
Clara's father attacked me and my husband.
We had to kill him and all his family
to prevent further plots and attacks.
And he still reached you here.
Don't you bear any grudge to Casimirus?
Everybody makes mistakes.
His had tragic results.
But he became more responsible and caring.
Though he was always brave.
I don't know what to with Yolanta.
Her presence here must be a burden for you.
This is not the child's fault.
Cudka promised she'll take care of her.
Watch out for Cudka, that's my advice.
- Look? - Where do you have it from?
My father gave me. Try it on.
And? Wait...
Can we talk?
Have you thought it over?
Will you accept my gift?
Yes and no.
I care about you.
That's why I'd like to be frank with you.
I'm counting on it.
I don't want to hurt you.
If it turned out that it's not love
I must be sure.
Cudka, even if you don't love me yet,
I'll do all I can for you to love me.
Don't let her think too long.
Thinking and love don't go together.
Act or you'll lose her.
You've been overhearing.
We're friends for a long time.
I can't watch you suffer from love.
You go to Pelka now and ask
for his daughter's hand.
Then, you go to Cudka at
once and propose to her.
I know what I'm saying.
It's useless. I can't do it.
A little bit of patience.
Everybody was a novice one day.
But, understand, I can only trade.
Calm down, I'll show you again, look.
Come on.
With clay... you need to work gently...
You need to listen to it
and it will lead you.
It will drive me crazy!
It's all because of my bad luck.
My husband was killed,
my goods were stolen.
Why?
Try again. Look!
I don't want!
I don't know if I can marry him.
Though I like him very much.
Love will come with time.
No. I...
I love the king.
So do I.
Do you know what queen Elizabeth told me?
In the modern courts in France or Italy,
more rhythmic and pleasant
music is in fashion.
They play and sing not
only for God's glory.
Gentlemen! I'd like to speak
to you, knight Pelka.
I'm listening, knight Niemierza.
Personally, if possible.
Gentlemen!
To love the king is not a sin but a duty.
We all love him because he's clever, brave
and does his best to improve our lives.
This is the king's duty.
The subject's duty is to
respect him and love him.
So, I'm not a sinner if I love him?
No, as long as we talk about pure love.
I could kiss the earth on which he steps.
It's adorable you want to serve him.
I'll do everything for him.
Good.
Tell me something about your knight.
He's gentle, nice...
He loves me, I know it.
He sometimes acts like
crazy, but he's a good boy.
He never gives up without a fight.
It's hard not to love him.
So, you see. Your own heart
has told you the way.
I know it's pure. I'm certain.
You'd better not tempt the king
with your beauty and devotion.
Don't distract him from
his destiny and duty.
So, I am to marry Niemierza
because of the king?
First of all, pray sincerely.
In your heart.
You'll get the answer.
Will you give me your daughter's hand?
I love her more than anything
and I promise to do
anything to make her happy.
I don't own much.
But I'll do my best for
her not to lack anything.
I know you'll be good to her.
Does it mean yes?
I'll give you my blessing.
Thank you!
- But there's one condition. - What?
My daughter must decide herself
if she wants to marry you.
She experienced a lot. She
lost her mother and brothers.
I want her to be happy.
So, I won't force her to do anything.
Nobody should be forced to get married.
It's bliss to love and to be loved.
If Cudka agrees to marry you, I'll give you
the village I got from king Vladislav.
Damn!
You're doing well.
Look! A little bird.
A nice bird, but you
can't eat soup from it.
Children would like it.
It could be painted and
they could play with it.
I'm not sure...
I don't have kids myself.
God didn't bless me.
But my neighbor has to give something to
her kids all the time to keep them busy.
Sometimes a spoon, sometimes a mug.
Why can't it be a clay bird?
Another jug...
If you keep doing like this,
we'll run out of dishes soon.
- I'm sorry. - It's all right.
It's not. I don't know
what's wrong with me today.
I burned the beans for pig ears.
Come on, pig ears. Nobody eats it here.
But we do in Lithuania.
I've been waiting for so long to prepare
a real Lithuanian feast for my lady.
And what now? We'll serve only kibinai.
And the Hungarian goulash
that burns tongues.
Come on, nobody will even try it.
And if they do, they'll be sorry at once.
I'll make broth with those ears.
Arunas!
/Lithuanian/ - What do you want?
- Get ready!
/Lithuanian/ You're going to Krakow
with prince Kestutis tomorrow.
/Lithuanian/ The road is dangerous.
/Lithuanian/ The prince needs
goods warriors with him.
/Lithuanian/ I'll go with Kestutis
everywhere, but not there.
/Lithuanian/ That's an order.
/Lithuanian/ You've got no choice.
Look! I baked them.
Beautiful!
You'll see! The whole Krakow is
going to talk about my birds.
I'll go to the inn to sell them.
There are Hungarians there,
and they may like them.
Maybe you open a stall? With toys?
- A stall? - Yes!
And what's this for?
You're so good to me.
As never before.
I'm going to have a stall.
Toys... People will buy...
I'll quickly make enough
for votives for my Martin.
I want this list of penalties to
be read to all people of Krakow.
Let everyone know there will be
no mercy for bandits and thieves.
Excuse me, sire, this may not
be an appropriate moment.
We need to improve the
condition of the treasury.
What's your advice, chancellor?
Taxes have to be collected
more effectively.
I'll ask my sister how
Charles Robert does it.
Have you got other issues? The
feast starts in a moment.
We need a new cup-bearer.
And the young Ligenza? The
widow was to send her son.
He's coming to us from Bologna.
- He studied? - Yes, sire.
It's too late for me to do it...
One more time.
That's all right.
It was good. We just don't have
enough opportunity to dance.
But dance is not a sin.
Of course, not.
You play beautifully, Yolanta.
Dad, you didn't see how beautifully
we danced with Kundzia.
There will be problems.
The guests can't stop praising your dishes.
No wonder if they fasted so much...
No, it's your dishes...
I only finished the dessert. How about it?
Beautiful!
And the rest? We need to
bring it to the tables!
Beautiful!
/praying in Latin/
We can't pray because Anna wants to dance.
The joy of life is expressed in
dance and it's pleasing to God.
I'm mourning and want to be respected.
The resurrection of Jesus
Christ overcomes death
and changes it into the miracle of life.
It seems for them the time for
resurrection has already come.
/praying in Latin/
Hard times are coming.
Isn't all of this waste of money?
But you liked the wine,
didn't you, excellency?
Lady, you inspired these
walls with life and beauty.
You can see they're inhabited
by people, not ghosts.
I only brought a little wine.
I heard, lady, you helped our countrymen
find a new home at the Hungarian court.
It's pleasure to support
those who deserve it.
I came only to try the
wine Elizabeth brought.
Sit, please.
Cudka,
my love
will you be my wife?