And this was a cuckold...
Whoever calls the king a "cuckold" one
more time, will lose their tongue and job.
They're talking about me. I know it.
I'm innocent but everybody
thinks I'm a harlot.
Ignore it, queen.
She didn't have a proof.
She knew she'd lose.
But she preferred to hurt me with slander.
The king supports you and
that's what matters.
Father, who's the clown
accompanying the king?
Mykanda of the Battle-axe coat of arms.
Was he entrusted by king Vladislav with
protecting Casimirus at the battle of Plowce?
King, this is your first official document.
An extension of the truce.
I hope it will make the kingdom stronger.
- Jasko, you'll go to Torun with it.
- Yes, sire.
Won't bishop Grot be disappointed?
I understand his position and
I hope he understands mine.
Gregory, stay at Wawel.
I need a good chamberlain of the court.
King! Because of him you're
called a coward in whole Europe.
Battle-axe at the court?
I'm not afraid of rumours.
And I need friends.
If I hadn't taken Casimirus
from the battlefield,
you'd be serving a different king today.
You were protecting your own head.
I was saving the future king.
You saved you damned butt!
And now the king's son's called a coward!
Better a coward than a corpse.
Easy, gentlemen. Now we've
got a different problem.
Holy Spirit dictated this to you, lady.
And this Spirit taught me a lot about life.
But Casimirus prefers making mistakes to
learning from his mother how to avoid them.
Mother...
I have to go back to Visegrad
as soon as possible.
Charles insists on the engagement
between little Andrew and Joanna,
the prince of Calabria's daughter.
Is it bad? You wanted to
marry him off to an Italian.
I heard she's a very quarrelsome person.
You must be cautious when
choosing a wife for your son.
More cautious than me.
Elizabeth, I'll be missing you very much.
I regret to go too.
Especially that I've got a
coronation gift for Casimirus.
A gift?
Kunegunda and I brought jesters to Krakow.
A jester troupe. Isn't it
entertainment for the rabble?
Joy as a gift is good for
anyone to start ruling.
Make sure they hold a show.
- Why me?
- Nobody's more respected than you here.
And this is this big problem?
That queen Jadwiga had an unhappy
face during the coronation?
It's hard for her to give up the
crown that she strove for so much.
The rumours about the new queen
seem to be a bigger problem.
With all due respect... But it's queen
Jadwiga who made these accusations.
Does this mean queen Aldona and queen
mother don't hold each other in esteem?
Beautifully said.
It's hard for her to accept
the loss of position.
The adultery trial only
added fuel to the fire.
Tell everybody that if anyone accuses my wife
of infidelity will be expelled from the court.
King, I heard there will
be jesters at the feast.
Even maids know about it, and I don't.
Queen, I'll take care of this
when we finish, all right?
Not now, excuse me.
Let me guess, the king
has important matters.
The king has his matters and I have mine.
Sometimes ours.
I understand. I know what it
means to be the king's wife.
Is it easier when you're not?
At last!
Lady, forgive me it took so long.
Catherine, I'm happy you're here.
I need support so much now.
I lost my husband, home, crown.
I'm left with nothing.
Nothing? Except for the son
who has just been crowned?
The family near you? What else
does a woman of our age need?
Gentlemen, stop it!
Do you want to show the king
how a hare hunts for a hound?
Have you got a better idea?
You'll run after your butt to Czechia if
we can't come up with anything better.
We have to perform something.
If we don't pay the inn-keeper
today, he'll kick us out.
I can't sleep outside. I've got lumbago.
- Innkeeper! - yes?
- Give us a moment!
What's going on at Wawel? What
are the hot topics there?
Whether to bathe in hot or cold water.
It's the most boring kingdom in the world.
Queen Elizabeth promised a good pay.
Do you want to know
what's going on at Wawel?
I'll tell you. If you drink with me.
What are you doing?
I know I shouldn't. You
don't need my sorcery.
I wanted to secure this place before I go.
Egle, what are you talking about?
I'm going back to Lithuania,
with your brothers.
I won't let you go anywhere.
You are as dear as mother to me.
I'd better take Lithuanian
ghosts away from here.
There's a Lithuanian queen
on the Polish throne,
so Polish ghosts have to
accept Lithuanian ones.
Can brother Wojciech come in?
Yes, please.
I don't want to disturb. It's
the first day of your rule.
Only lords rule. Here...
Bitterness?
I thought everything will be
different after the coronation,
That something will change.
But this trial hurt me a lot.
On the contrary.
You admitted a mistake. It
was an act of great courage.
Rather of foolishness.
The queen will never forgive me.
She'll be very watchful now, but...
You have to watch your
every step and every word.
What am I to do?
Follow Christ.
He was good to his tormentors.
I'll never be good enough for her.
I don't know how to talk to her.
Have you tried?
Try. Now you've got the crown.
Start using it.
It was great honour meeting you.
I hope we'll meet again.
I'll be happy to come to Vilnius
for your baptism, prince.
The I'll ask you to be my godmother.
Can you do me this favor, queen?
Certainly!
Good bye, prince!
Lady!
Be careful!
The last thing we need is her jealous
husband with an army at our borders.
A wonderful woman.
Beautiful, brave, wise.
Our Aldona should be like this.
Our sister doesn't lack
beauty, courage or anything.
But she's too honest.
The court is a nest of wasps.
You need to know how to treat them
so that they don't sting you.
Elizabeth knows this.
Don't you wonder why she got close to you?
I don't know.
It's not about you, can't you see?
She'd like to baptize us.
She'd earn favour from the pope.
And why do you think I'm doing this?
When I praise her, she stands by
Aldona against her own mother.
You'd better look for Arunas
instead of teaching me.
If he decided to hide, we're
on a wild goose chase.
Nobody will find him.
You have green fingers.
I lived in a forest.
I believed it has divine powers.
God's present in all existence.
Really? You won't find Him in some people.
Everybody's got their weaknesses. You too.
I thought of moving you to Swiety
Krzyz or even Monte Cassino.
Please, don't.
I've got to stay here to
fight against temptation.
Not just run away from it.
I want to sacrifice my love to God.
I want to heal people.
Leave healing to God.
And me? When will He heal me?
From this love.
Have you chosen your conventual name?
Remind me...
the name of the man who
helped Jesus carry the cross.
Simon.
I'd like to have this name.
You're still occupying the royal chambers.
You don't use a weapon but
you can have it your way.
The sword is not as handy as the mind.
Vladislav admired you so much.
When he stayed with us,
he talked only about you.
He didn't even look at any young girl.
How I envied you...
He always preferred
politics to bed-chamber.
I've never met a man who'd talk
about his wife with such devotion.
How well you brought up the children,
How you hid with them,
How you led the defence of Wawel.
Queen, I beg for forgiveness.
I was so scared you'd
expel me from the court
that I lost my senses.
Go away if you have
nothing important to say.
Queen Anna... Nobody wants to
listen to her at the court.
And she wastes the royal funds...
I counted myself. She sent people on
errands to town seven times yesterday.
The king has the right to have
fun in a royal way. Leave us.
What happened? You used
to praise her so much.
She said she saw Anna with a Lithuanian
knight and later she denied it.
I told everybody to make an oath.
Are you suspecting Anna of infidelity?
She swore she was faithful to her husband.
Did you believe her?
Casimirus did and it's enough for me.
How will you live under the same roof now?
After such an event...
Here's my son's wife.
Your highness, do you
remember Catherine Pilecka?
Of course.
Excuse me, lady, but can
we talk face to face?
Of course.
Yes.
Queen, the whole court
is buzzing with gossip.
Advise me, please, what to do.
Are you asking me for advice?
You agreed to pass your crown to me.
I know how much it meant to you, Mother.
Behave flawlessly. Don't lose your temper.
Keep your head up. You're not blaming
yourself for anything, are you?
Forgive me I doubted your fidelity.
I'm glad you believed, after all.
Was this Lithuanian knight dear to you?
Casimirus is my husband, and
nobody else matters to me.
Child, I'm happy you say so.
I see Casimirus is very happy.
You gave him two daughters.
All you lack is a son.
Casimirus comes more often
to my chamber recently.
Does he? I'm happy to hear that.
Catherine's waiting for me.
Queen...
I apologize for anything that
offended you for all those years.
Forgive me, I always meant well...
The rules of the court are
difficult and not natural for me.
I admire how easily you adjusted
to them because I can't.
That's why I'm asking you for help...
My child!
I have a request to you.
I'd like to stay in my chamber.
Opposite the king's? And me?
I think my son will find a
way to you even in the dark.
The feast is coming. I have to prepare...
A comedy show.
My daughters know how to add
splendour to the celebration.
They learnt this from
you, Mother, didn't they?
Did Mother really kiss you?
And she even called me queen...
You see? She's changing because of you.
Not enough to move out of her bed chamber.
Everything will be fine.
Will you persuade her to move?
Not today.
Let's have fun.
Long live king Casimirus.
Long live queen Anna.
Honourable guests, princes, courtiers...
It's great joy to carry
the burden of the crown.
You share everyday hardships with me,
today, let's rejoice!
But, theatre first!
It's a gift from the king's sisters
for his coronation.
Play the fanfares for the artists.
We must fulfill queen mother's request.
The play is called... "A Little Snare".
It takes place far, far away...
In the faraway China,
where emperor Cock-A-Doodle-Doo
and empress Cha-Caw
decided to marry off
their son, Little One
Wife, agree to marry off our son at last!
Little One is still a child.
He's 40 years old!
Exactly, a child!
It's time for him to have his own children,
to stop sleeping in the
cradle in our bed chamber.
All right. On one condition...
I'll pick a wife for him myself.
Little One, put this iron
away or you'll get hurt!
He got dirty! Mummy will clean!
Mummy will clean!
Mother, did you agree for this?
The mother found the best
candidates in the kingdom.
What's your dowry, miss?
The woman's deaf!
You are a chef!
I'm saying you can't hear.
Mice? They're near?
Where?
Daddy? It's not time for me to marry.
Mice!
Son, don't worry.
The next candidate will be younger.
What's your dowry, beautiful lady?
Three cartloads of gold.
Did you hear that son?
Go, meet your future wife.
Come back to me, my husband!
And he ran away from his wife.
- If he gets hurt when hunting? - Hurt...
- If he falls down? - Falls down...
- If he gets injured? - Injured...
- Gets a cold? - A cold...
I told you husband, Little One
is not ready for a marriage.
I know.
We'll enlarge our chamber so that
he can stay with us for ever.
No, no!
Thank you, sire, for bringing me here.
I'm the emperor's son. Be my wife!
You have to defeat my fiancee first.
I wield an axe the best in China,
I can shoot an arrow behind the Great Wall.
I'll best him at sword and dice.
How about singing?
I'm too nervous for that...
Good bye...
/singing/
I've lost...
the duel for a wife.
More beautiful than dawn...
So similar to you, Mother.
To me? Impossible, my son's hallucinating.
Don't worry, Little One. I'm
with you and I'll always be.
What is it? Poison?
I prefer to die rather than
live without my beauty.
I feel I must sing!
/singing/
No, Mother, don't sing!
It's a wonderful medicine.
It cures voice and mind.
My husband, the emperor, was right. I
have to give you back to your wife.
Even stupid geese let their
goslings leave the nest.
For the wedding gift, I'll give you
whole China... to the Great Wall!
What happened, castellan?
A bunch of fools!
A sense of humour is a sign of intellect.
And what if people learn about it?
When they start talking about it in Europe?
Both Jadwiga and Casimirus
had a good laugh.
Drink some mead and at least
pretend the comedians amused you.
They didn't!
As I said. Only smart people
have a sense of humour.
Right!
Tired?
The air is stifling, isn't it?
Catherine, tell me if, in your opinion,
I'm embarrassing my son.
Motherly love can't embarrass...
I've never seen a comedy like that.
Is this really how simple folks see me?
Nonsense! Drink your herbs!
They laughed at me.
People will laugh even at a bear's show.
They need entertainment.
What did they call this play?
"A Little Snare"?
Yes.
Very clever.
Love is such a little snare.
I think Anna completely ensnared Casimirus.
There's only one way to help
my son rule peacefully.
I'll need your help.
What do you want to do?
I have a plan.