This is your dowry.
A bit far from Krakow.
Why do you need Krakow?
You'll be a wife, a mother...
You'll have a lot to do.
You'll build a house...
bring up my grandchildren.
Father, when you started the family,
how did you know what you felt was love?
Love will always prevail.
Like grass. An army can march over it,
fire, water... It will always recover.
But it's got to be true.
- And from here... - I love Niemierza.
Love is about standing by
somebody, whatever happens.
I'd like to live here with Yolanta.
I want you to bring my
grandchildren on my land.
I saw the way you look at Casimirus.
Do you want to follow the
little girl's mother's fate?
Be careful, daughter.
I won't do anything that
may make you ashamed.
I know.
But be careful.
It's great joy to be at
your coronation, Casimirus.
Krakow impressed us a lot.
Vilnius is like a younger brother.
Maybe it will catch up with the older soon?
Arunas, you must admit
the castle's impressive.
It's easier to get lost here
than in a Lithuanian forest.
I don't get lost in a forest.
Your castle, sire, is a bit intimidating...
Kestutis?
You didn't say your brother's so handsome.
When I last saw him he was
shorter and slimmer than me.
I was missing you too.
There was nobody to challenge
when practicing the bow.
There's no better archer in Lithuania.
Maybe, except Arunas. Do you remember him?
Give it to me, I'll hang it.
I'll bring something to eat.
Are you from far away, miss?
Can't you help me with something, miss?
I've got six kids at home. Starving.
Have mercy, lady.
I've got nothing, I'm sorry.
You've got something, anyway.
Give it back to her, good man.
Easy.
My lord...
Leave him!
Father!
Don't leave me, Father!
Help me, man! Save him!
You are so much like her...
Don't leave me, Father...
Queen Jadwiga!
Sit down, please.
I want everybody to feel like at home.
I've got to talk to him.
With whom?
You know very well. Help me.
No.
I'll talk to him.
It will only make him angry. You know him.
I do. And I know you too.
I remember how you sneaked out together,
against everybody and everything.
Quiet!
Pour!
Nobody can learn about me and him.
I've got to talk to him.
It won't end well.
Sit down, child.
Helen...
I know how hard it is for you to be
far from your family, your mother.
And being a lady-in-waiting
is sometimes difficult.
It's great honour.
I know I can rely on you.
I can, can't I? You're honest, sincere
you got good upbringing.
Thank you, lady.
I know you'll understand my... concerns.
The coronation's coming soon,
there are more and more
strangers at the court...
I want to you to keep an eye on Anna.
It's for her benefit. And yours.
- Mine? - Yes. As her maid,
you're responsible for her.
So, be watchful, please.
Very watchful.
Day and... night.
What happened?
Have you seen a ghost?
Arunas?
Leave us alone, Egle.
The queen can be alone
with a male stranger.
I'm not a stranger, Egle.
You know me since I was a child.
And what if somebody learns you're here?
Make sure nobody does.
I thought you're wiser.
Why did you come here?
I had no choice.
They say you've got no wife
or children, is it true?
Yes, true.
Why? You're free.
I burned the snake pendant I got from you.
Arunas, we were children.
It's time you forget me
and start living your own life.
You think I didn't marry because of you.
I saw why you left.
You gave him children.
I had no choice.
I can't remember you
resisted this marriage much.
You let yourself be sold.
For this...
How can you say so?
You had no choice!
And what choice was that...
Between a pauper and a king?
My father would never agree
for us to be together.
You didn't use to listen
to your father so much.
But it was before you learnt
you'd become a queen.
If only I had had another choice...
You had.
What do you want?
Queen Elizabeth is coming here.
Careful!
I'm here.
What happened?
Bandits attacked us.
Bring him to my chamber, quickly!
You have to try the dresses before the
maids start sewing in the ornaments.
Now?
Don't stand like a tailor's
dummy, help her take it off.
With such body, you don't need to
give your husband an aphrodisiac.
A man doesn't need much. You'll
just show your bare arm.
Heavy...
Being a woman is not light, and
being a queen is even heavier.
Embroidered rose bushes will be here,
each with three golden leaves.
Then branches with pearls, and...
Beautiful!
It will be finished with gold and silver.
Here, embroidered clover.
You need magic fingers for all of this.
I'm sorry...
You can do without them.
Luckily, a woman's love is shown
not only with her fingers
but also the eyes, mouth and
even the tip of her toe.
Unlike a man's love, which
grows only in his...
What?
You need to know something
before your wedding.
You give your husband ecstasy, and
he'll stay put by your bed like a dog.
Solid work, potter.
And what's that?
Birds.
Very smart.
Children should see it.
I don't have children.
The little princesses!
Why may children need clay birds?
Live ones are nicer.
All children, royal or
peasant, like to play!
What an idea! I am to
bring clay birds to kids.
They'll be happy.
We need to pay.
- How much? - 10 groszes each.
I'd buy two pots for this money!
All right. I'll pay.
I though he'd try to bargain!
The end price is 3 groszes.
We women must help each other.
Thank you.
Turn a little.
It will pinch a little...
It's nothing for a knight, though...
Are you all right?
Hush! Leave him alone.
He needs to rest.
You're going to make it.
I'm so afraid.
Easy.
Tell me he's not going to die, please.
Tell me, I don't want to be alone.
You won't. I'll always be with you.
Is Pelka wounded?
Elias is dressing his wounds.
It's amazing the king had
time to visit my father.
Your father is not just a knight.
Still, it's amazing...
For my father, it must be important.
Because of the marriage
of Aldona and Casimirus,
we're closer to the Christian world.
Don't tell me you want to be baptized.
I want our people to have a better life.
Is it bad?
Our people love, dance, enjoy themselves.
Here they'd be better off
without this Calvary.
I want to see Krakow
from the tallest tower.
Have you seen Arunas, where is he?
- He should see it.
- He must have got lost.
It's his first time in such a castle.
We'll find him.
He was to visit places with us.
Learn courtly manners.
Everything is different and new for him.
He's my bravest man but he
cringed the moment he saw Wawel.
/Lithuanian/ Find Arunas!
Don't get up.
Elias let me stay here if
you promise not to get up.
Where's my daughter?
With Niemierza.
Forgive my insolence...
but I have to ask you for something...
Whatever you want.
Make sure she marries him.
He won't hurt her.
You're talking as if you were to die.
The wound is deep.
Are you in a hurry?
Wouldn't you prefer to
dance on her wedding?
Promise me.
I'll make sure Cudka marries Niemierza.
I'll supply them with everything.
I'll do everything for
your daughter to be happy.
I'll send a maid with whiting.
Elizabeth, thank you.
Helena, I thank you too.
I didn't stop thinking of you.
I can't.
Someone can come in here anytime.
Meet me at night.
You're stronger.
You've got shape too.
You peeped.
Find one man who'd hold himself.
I'll keep this picture
in my mind till I die.
Go now.
Wait for me at the Eastern Gate.
Arunas!
I've been waiting for this for a long time.
I married somebody else.
You're mine and you will.
- I swore to God. - Their god. Not ours.
Now, mine too.
Don't you remember when we
made sacrifice to Perkunas?
This was before I got to know the real god.
Have you seen him?
No.
So, how do you know he's real?
From here. Faith doesn't come
from your head, but your heart.
So does love.
For all this time, I haven't
touched another woman.
Do you love me?
Are you still asking?
When I'm next to you and I hear your voice,
I have less and less strength...
So, if you really love me,
lead me not into temptation.
God wouldn't forgive me, nor Casimirus.
I can't.
Father, how are you?
When I see you, I feel better at once.
You're so beautiful...
Guard her, boy.
Like the apple of my eye.
- Does it hurt? I'll call Elias. - No.
All's in God's hands.
Maybe He will let me see
my grandchildren first,
before He summons me.
Helen, speak, please.
I followed Anna.
Speak, for God's sake.
I saw her... with a Lithuanian.
Did Anna betray Casimirus?
Helen, if you want to stay at the
court, you have to tell the truth.
Did Anna betray my son?
I knew it.
She can't become the queen.
God! What will happen now?
Don't talk to anybody about it, even Jasko.