God, take this love away from me.
It brings me only suffering.
He belongs to another one.
Cudka!
Father!
You've returned!
Mum, there's somebody there, look!
Nobody's there, sleep!
It's too early to get up.
/singing a lullaby/
That's you...
And who did you expect?
Easy. You're safe.
I won't let anybody get hurt.
Nobody wanted to tell me where you went...
or when you'd return.
You've been away for so long.
Snow blocked the roads to Visegrad.
I was afraid I'd lose you.
Promise you'll not leave me alone again.
Child, you know it's not up to me.
But I may stay in Krakow long enough
to get you a good pair of shoes.
Has anybody seen a lady
running barefoot in Wawel?
I've got shoes, but I couldn't find them.
I was in such a hurry to see you.
I didn't want to wake you, but I
wanted to make sure you're safe.
I can't stand the thought our
daughters could have been poisoned.
Whatever are they doing here?
Are you surprised I wanted them
with me after all of this?
Royal children sleep in their own bed.
In Lithuania a home is a home.
Even the richest one.
And kids can play and hug their mother.
Maybe if it weren't for these cold
walls, you'd be different too?
Different?
Kunegunda, get up!
It's always a war, or
Lent, and now the kids...
Lady, the bells for matins...
Again, I dreamt of...
Who?
My children.
Everybody's abandoning me.
Enemies all around.
Were Vladislav alive, he'd know what to do.
And if he didn't know, he
would ask your advice.
Forgive, my lady.
My tongue's quicker than mind.
If my son was willing to
listen to me, like my husband
there wouldn't be this mess now.
But Casimirus want to rule by himself,
without my support.
He wants to prove he's the king.
He's completely different from Vladislav.
Therefore I pray for him all the time.
Pelka says Elizabeth and her court
will be here at any moment.
Why wasn't I sent for?
Pelka arrived in the middle of the night.
You were asleep.
That's what I'm talking about.
We have to prepare the funeral,
receive the guests, provide security.
Do you know what would happen if the
Hungarian queen was poisoned at Wawel?
They caught the poisoners,
they're in the vault.
How do you know these are all of them?
Do we know who's behind them?
We'll get to know
It's enought to interrogate
them well, torture a little...
Later. Now we need to prepare Wawel.
Let me out, people help me!
Quiet, man!
I can't listen to this anymore.
You scream for the whole night, like crazy.
It may be my last sunrise...
I don't want to die...
Please, knight!
Here, sit at the table.
Give us groats with dressing!
Bring salted fish and slice bread!
Don't trouble yourself, cook master.
I'll eat anything.
The prince said I need to receive
you as a distiguished guest.
I'd be happy to eat our
beer soup with cheese.
I was thinking of it during the
whole way back from Visegrad.
Soup? Here you are!
Hold on!
They say there are now
poisons you can't smell.
It's just cooked.
You can eat it. Nobody's going
to get poisoned with my soup.
Who'd like to poison me?
Do I disturb anybody?
Casimirus's children aren't safe.
Somebody tried to poison them yesterday.
Holy Mary, why?
Luckily, nobody got hurt and the
poisoners are already in the vault.
You must have no conscience
to hurt innocent children.
They'll pay for that with their heads.
And the executioner will
add extra pain first.
All right, get down to work!
The fish won't cook by itself and
neither will the cabbage slice.
Tell us how they fed you in Hungary.
Is it true everything's so spicy there?
Once I even had tears in my
eyes, my tongue was burning!
What can I give them here?
They've been on the way for two weeks.
When they arrive, they'll
be so tired and hungry
that any food will make them happy.
So, maybe our cuisine?
Polish!
I can't believe the queen misses
all the cabbage or sour soups.
Everything's so sour here
that your mouth hurts.
I'll start squinting and salivating,
maybe they'll think I'm too
stupid for a conspiracy...
and they'll let me go...
Casimirus won't bother.
He's got neither heart nor honour.
First, he raped Zach's daughter and
the murdered the whole family,
so that he could flee from justice.
Yeah, raped...
Don't try to wriggle from the executioner.
Or he'll make you suffer
cutting your head off.
One stroke.
Even if I starved, I'll never
again take what's not mine,
and I'll be fasting...
just let me live a little more.
Is something bothering you, daughter?
I'm all alone here.
Alone?
I know well you've got
someone in your heart.
I talked to him about you.
But I won't give my daughter away easily.
I must be sure Niemierza
will take good care of you.
Niemierza?
Aren't you curious what's
going on with him?
We haven't been engaged,
so I'm ashamed to ask.
I though you like him.
You probably like the
prince, my lady, don't you?
All women, ladies-in-waiting and chambermaids
alike, follow him with their eyes.
I saw a picture of St. Sebastian,
pierced with arrows here...
I thought I'd never see
a man more handsome.
But, Casimirus is in a different league...
The dough for cake isn't ready!
The fish isn't cleaned!
And you came here for a chat!
Praised be God and all saints!
Forever and ever.
I have to go back to my lady.
Your daughter's beautiful.
It's good she's like her mother and not me.
Why did queen Elizabeth linger for so long
before coming to her father's funeral?
When I arrived in Visegrad, she was sick.
The medics wouldn't let her go.
Here...
No, we're still before the mass.
The funeral procession is today, isn't it?
The rich and the commonners will be able to
see off the king in all churches of Krakow.
Then I'll go too.
No, you take a rest.
You've been travelling for a week.
I owe my king much more.
And this little I can do,
pray and join the procession.
First, there will ba carts,
each with four horses
Everything as you wished, lady,
dressed in black cloth
Later mourners and mounted
knights in full armour
How about monastery congregations?
All clergymen in town are waiting,
singing mourning songs.
Later the black cloth has to be
shared by churches and monasteries
Somebody has to give alms to the poor,
so that they pray for the late king's soul.
Maybe Pelka?
Where's Kundegunda?
Find her, please!
Will you let him die?
You're my cousin!
Leave me alone, woman. Beer!
Have mercy, man. Save Martin!
What will I do without him?
Is he the only man in the world?
You'll find a better one.
After all these wars, only the ugly, the
lame or the old are left in Krakow.
Oh yeah, it must be hard to find such
a bum and drunkard like your Martin.
I'll be delighted to cut
this scum's head off.
Do you know why no woman wants you?
Because you're only good for
murder and carrion collection...
Not for love...
What am I to do?
What if something happened
to her or she was kidnapped?
At Wawel, how come?
And how come murderes
found the way to here?
Yolanta!
Why are you hiding here?
Everybody's looking for you.
Mom says grandpa is among angels now,
and the bishop says he'll turn to ash.
So, what will happen to him?
Come, they're waiting for us.
I don't want to go to angels and
I don't want to turn to ash.
What ideas are those?
Because if I turn to ash,
I won't be there anymore.
Only the body dies.
The soul is immortal.
You'll leave the body like an old dress,
and you'll fly straight to God!
Naked?
God, what am I to do?
Martin...
My love!
I brought you bread.
Thank you!
Get me out of here!
How?
How? How?!
They'll cut my hands off, impale
me, and dismember my body...
What can I do?
Pray only, so that the devil
doesn't take you to hell.
I've paid for a mass for you.
And I paid the rest to the
guards to let me in here...
and say goodbye...
I don't want to die...
Aren't you ashamed of
crying in front of a woman?
What man are you?
A man... full of life!
You devil!
My death actually suits you...
Do you want to get rid of me?
You lost your mind out of fear.
My bedsheet hasn't cooled yet,
and you're already looking for another man?
How dare you? I'm a decent woman.
I swore to you.
I swear to you too, I won't
leave you even after... death.
Martin, for God's sake,
what are you saying?
I'll come back from the nether
world as an evil spirit,
and I'll make sure no man
replaces me in your bed...
And, because you let them behead
me, I'll rattle with chains,
so that you'll never sleep till you die.
Brother...
If it wasn't for you, I'd
be preparing a funeral
not only for my father,
but also for my children.
Let Wawel be your second home.
Aren't you afraid of having
a pagan as your brother?
My daughters are half-Lithuanian
and half-Christian.
Your sister has also been baptized.
Perhaps you'll convert too?
I'll send for Giediminas to Lithuania.
I want all my friends to be
with me during the coronation.
And I'll pray for your imminent baptism.
Will you get baptized?
Who knows?
The act of conversion requires time.
Sure...
I know you want the best of both worlds.
The pope and the patriarch.
Whatever, when we were kids
you always cheated everybody at dice.
It's not only me who wants
the best of both worlds.
Praised be Jesus Christ.
Forever and ever.
I heard the Hungarian
court is coming to Wawel.
Don't you need something?
I can fix anything.
How much?
A little help.
Bring me to the chancellor or
pass a good word on my behalf.
I've got so much work I
don't know where to start
and now the chancellor...
Please, it's a matter of life and death.
Come later, when everything's more quiet.
After the funeral, after the coronation.
It will be too late.
The chancellor needs more beer, quickly!
Open the new barrel!
Praised be God!
Are you preparing it for the chancellor?
Everybody's hungry and thirsty
after the procession.
Have they finished?
They have. It was beautiful.
What weeping, what lament!
And what complaints from
the lords and the clergy!
The human tongue can't express it.
Lord, have mercy! Spare Martin's life.
He may be a drunkard but not murderer.
Are you Martin's wife?
Yes! He's innocent.
It's me. I ordered him to find a job.
Now he's in the vault because of me.
The law is harsh but it is the law.
Whoever betrayed the king must be beheaded.
Sire, I beg you! Don't
torture him at least.
- Take her! - Don't torture him!
Don't pull out his teeth and nails!
Have mercy!
He won't stand it!
How did she get in here?
Stupid woman! Do you want
to lose your head too?
I don't care...
They're going to kill Marcin.
It's as if they killed me.
What life is it without husband?
You'll find another...
Sure...
When, at night, Marcin will rattle
chains and keep me awake...
I prefer to jump to the river...
What's with her?
She's running as if chased
by some evil spirit...
What have you done to her?
I?
Damned men!
You're only pain in the neck!
Stop this sorcery, Egle.
You can't believe in two gods.
Or love two men.
That's only a childhood souvenir.
He's still waiting for you.
He'd better forget about me.
Mum...
I'm here.
Are you better?
If I were a man,
you'd be sitting by my side night
and day, like by the father's.
But you're not dying.
What's my fault?
That I wasn't born a boy?
You can't change the way the river flows
or the woman's fate.
So, stop complaining or
you'll die of bitterness.
You're most like me of all my children.
I knew you could achieve more.
That's why I demanded more from you.
Your highness, queen Elizabeth
and her court are in Opatowiec.
So, she's going to be in
Krakow in a day or two.
Are the rooms ready for her court?
Egle, what can you see?
Are we in danger?
Giltine.
The godess of death?
Somebody's going to die?
Egle?