This is the year 1332.
It has been seven years since the wedding of Casimirus and Anna.
The couple has already got two daughters, Elizabeth and Kunegunda.
There is a war between Poland
and the Teutonic Order,
and John of Bohemia makes a
claim to the Polish crown.
Despite the victory at
the battle of Plowce,
king Vladislav loses
Kuyavia and Dobrzyn Land,
and the Czech king effortlessly made vassals of Silesian and Mazovian princes,
who invade the lands of the kingdom of Poland.
Vladislav and Casimirus retaliate against them.
After two years of war expedition, the father and the son return to Krakow...
Lord, I thank you for their happy return.
I thank you for my children.
Thank you for Casimirus, for his wife,
for their two daughters.
Oh Lord, you know how much Vladislav wanted to regain his home land.
He wanted so much.
And it didn't happen...
Why?
Why didn't you help him?
Why are you angry?
All right! It's beautiful, leave it!
You haven't seen your husband for so long, my lady.
And he hasn't seen you.
You have to look beautiful.
Don't punish us, Lord!
I beg you!
Help us finish the reunification.
And protect my son, Casimirus.
Mom, quickly, we're running to greet Daddy!
How ugly!
Mom, what is it?
It's Givate, the good snake, the guardian of the forest.
In my country, Lithuania, people believe it has got special powers.
You mustn't believe in such things! You go to hell for it!
But it's not a sin to know where you're from
it's only a childhood souvenir.
and Christ died on the cross for all people, including Lithuanians.
You're waiting for someone too, aren't you?
For my father.
Grandma!
Daddy and Grandpa have returned from the war.
Let's go to town to greet them!
You can't go to town now, but
you'll be invited to the welcome ceremony.
I promise...
But Grandma, why?
Girls, we have to prepare...
- I am prepared!
- But we have to correct it, come on.
- Please, come.
- No, no!
Anna...
Dress more modestly
There will be a ceremony
My lady, it's for the return of my beloved husband!
I understand, but you don't want him to think
you dressed like this when he was away.
Change this dress, please.
Is this Dad?
Yes, darling.
He didn't have a beard.
At war there's no time to shave.
Daddy!
Daddy, you were away for so long!
Don't fear.
Don't fear of anyone. Never!
Where's your sister?
Jadwiga!
Greetings, my wife!
Mother!
Greetings, son!
Pax vobiscum!
Thanks to God!
For the victories over the lords of Glogow.
for the capture of Koscian.
For defeating the Silesian princes.
Mother of Jesus Christ, the king of Nazareth.
Save the king of Poland,
Save his son, Casimirus
/praying in Latin/
- I'm going to the girls.
- Good. Dance.
Pelka, who's that girl?
Be careful.
She's not married?
It's my daughter.
I am Niewieza of Golcza, the royal knight.
At dusk, there will be a tournament. I'll win it for you.
Let me be your knight.
Look... I conquered a duchy
and I'm to weak to get up.
I'll help you.
Lean on my arm. Come.
Vladislav!
I want you to give me a son.
The heir.
So come to my bed tonight.
You've been away for two years.
At war, I got unused from gallantry.
But you captured Koscian, and the whole of Krakow is talking about it.
I won't boast about it.
Why not?
My father says
a modest ruler means a weak country.
And a cruel ruler?
I murdered like a butcher.
And a good ruler means a big war.
So, let's drink for war!
Lady!
Don't tell me... Don't tell me it's now...
It's... It's a bit better...
but the end is near...
The king reconciled with God...
Nobody can learn
about the king's illness...
Even the pope...
Only our children....
The king and queen are not here...
And your mother keeps an eye on me all the time...
Casimirus...
Your father is asking to see you.
I have visitors.
And where's the king?
Aren't he and his son preparing a new war?
The bishop of Krakow should know such things best.
They don't listen to the bishop.
Your husband slaughtered more than a hundred people in Koscian.
The king forbid it
but he went with the Hungarians and wiped them out.
Knights, Silesians, Czechs, Germans...
He spared nobody.
He slaughtered noblemen like cattle.
And what?
The town treasury was empty.
What victory is that?
Forgive me, bishop, but I'm going to dance.
Do you find people's death amusing?
I find your hypocrisy appalling.
Time has come for me, my son...
No, Father, not yet...
I've always been proud of you
I've never shown it to you.
but I've been...
Be a proud king
Good and proud.
I'll never be the king like you.
You will.
You'll be better.
You'll be great.
I'll never achieve what you did.
You regained the crown.
And you'll keep it.
You'll regain the lands which I couldn't regain.
You'll be a great king.
Father!
I saw how the prince greeted his wife upon his return.
He wasn't very effusive...
But she's his wife...
Because of this marriage we have peace in the east.
And, in spite of this...
In spite of this, aren't you happy, my lady
your son is Gediminas' daughter's husband?
I've never really accepted this.
Never.
But there's nothing you can do now.
You're wrong. I can.
I may not allow her to be crowned
when Casimirus becomes the king.
I'm wearing the crown.
Can I disagree to this?
I can!
Promise that when you're the queen, there will be more fun like this.
Do you like to play so much? Where's your knight?
He's getting ready for the tournament.
So, go, you have to be there, have fun, because lent is coming soon
and only prayers and mortification.
Thank you, my lady.
Wait!
First, find Egla and tell her to come here.
Yes, my lady.
Let's summon a medic.
The Benedictines of Tyniec can cure with herbs.
We can't summon anyone, this is the king's will.
Nobody can know of his ailment.
Even your wife.
He fell so suddenly.
It may be witchcraft.
Maybe someone bewitched him.
Since when do you believe in superstition?
You'd better pray for your father's health.
We need to bring your sisters.
You tell me to hide my father's condition from my wife
and you want to the Hungarian king know?
Not the king, but the queen.
Your sister, Elizabeth.
And Kunegunda will tell you
what's happening in Silesia.
What are the Czech king's intentions?
And you believe the sisters will keep the secret?
And our envoys?
You choose them - it will be your first decision.
It may decide your whole life.
Your future crown.
Why am I to say nothing to Anna?
Because there are two rulers on Earth.
who, for sure, mustn't know of the father's illness
The master of the Teutonic Order and the great prince of Lithuania.
- Your wife's father.
- No,no,no...
Anna will suspect something's wrong with the father.
It all depends on you.
You don't have to tell her everything
Be cautious.
Are there people you trust?
Yes.
So bring them.
And act...
Egle, are you sure the king's dying?
I knew they're hiding something from me.
Not only from you. They're hiding it from everybody.
Because they're afraid.
Yes, they are afraid that the enemies may learn about the king's illness.
Do you know what Jadwiga said?
That as long as she's alive, I won't be crowned.
You understand, Egle? I won't be the queen!
If I was the mother of the king's heir, I would be safe.
but, until I bear a son, I may be got rid of, sent away.
And even killed.
Egle, I need advice. What to do? How to defend myself?
You can't do it alone.
And your husband obeys his mother
My husband wouldn't let me get hurt.
But could he defend you?
Don't ask questions but tell me what to do!
Algirdas, your brother.
I don't understand?
Summon him to come here.
Let's say, to visit his sister.
You'll be safe with him by your side.
But how to let him know?
Only a trusted person can go to Lithuania.
You will go to Silesia, to my sister, Kunegunda.
And you, Pelka, to Visegrad, to the Hungarian queen, my sister, Elizabeth.
Nobody can learn about our mission. Nobody!
You'll carry letters.
They can't fall into the wrong hands.
You have to deliver them to my sisters in person, understand?
And when do we depart?
Today, immediately.
- But...
- What? Are you scared?
No!
So...
The fight is between
Stan of Kokorzyn
and Niemieza of Golcza.
Niemieza of Golcza?
Is he here, or is he a coward?
Wait here!
I lost my honour.
I didn't stand the ground.
They called me a coward.
And now I can't even explain why I did it.
You're given a secret mission in the king's service.
This is a great honour.
Have you sent for the sisters?
Elias is finishing the letters
They'll go soon.
They say you flinched at Plowce.
That you fled the battlefield...
They don't want to believe I ordered to send you away.
It was my mistake.
Don't let them call you a coward...
-Never.
- I won't let them.
And now, the death of the Zachs...
Unnecessary evil...
Unnecessary evil is pure evil.
Koscian is a different story...
It's war...
But the death of the Zachs'?
The eyes of the murdered will haunt you in your dreams.
Then, when you wake up,
think of the crown.
It'll give you some relief.
And remember,
You're the king of blood
and this obliges.
I'll probably go to the monastery.
What happened?
My knight didn't turn up for the fight. What embarrassment!
Oh well... Terrible, really!
Before you go to the monastery because of this, go to the kitchen and call my cook.
You're hungry, my lady. I'll fetch something.
Cudka...
Don't look for Niemieza, but bring the cook.
My king, it's ready. The seal.
On this sword...
on which king Vladislav made a pledge to the Polish crown.
You swear...
not to disclose to anybody
that the king lies ill in bed,
never to disclose to anybody
where you were sent
and that you'll sooner die than disclose the king's secrets.
I swear.
I'll sooner die.
- I'm here,my lady.
- Close the door.
Have you recently brought kindziukas from Lithuania?
It didn't taste good?
I'll order to boil this merchant alive.
with Polish borscht, so that he gets more fat.
Who is this merchant?
Can he be trusted?
I won't get tortured for him.
Is he still in Krakow?
What's his name? Is he Lithuanian?
Vytautas, my lady.
He was to bring amber to Hungary, but he sold it to Teutonic knights.
Disgrace, my lady. I didn't know anything about it.
This Vytautas has to do something for me.
Everything, my lady, for Perkunas (the god of thunder)
and for Jesus, but don't punish him, my lady!
He's my relative from Trakai.
Relative? Where's he sleeping?
At my place...
But we quarreled and he went away.
He must be sitting at the inn in town.
You'll give him this ring.
He must go quickly to Lithuania and give it to my brother, Algirdas.
He'll get a reward worth more than this ring.
And tell my brother I need his help.
Very well.
- Why did you flinch?
- I didn't.
- But I can't tell you why I withdrew.
- Tell me!
Or else, I won't forget you!
Cudka, what's going on here?
He's a coward... and a traitor!
He's brave and loyal.
Believe me.
I'm leaving, daughter. I don't know for how long.
Where?
Secret mission.
I can't say more.
I've been waiting for you.
My husband...
And you seem not happy to see me...
You left me alone at the feast.
Don't be angry, Anna
I come back from war, a wild man...
You make me blush.
I know... I neglected you...
But just say a word... What do you want?
A new horse?
A village?
A jewel?
Say what you want...
One dance...
I won't go. The prince will kill me.
- He knows I'm trading with Teutonic knights.
- He won't kill you.
You will give this ring to prince Algirdas.
It's a sign.
You'll pass the message and get a reward.
I had a dream
that Giediminas is attacking Krakow.
You don't need to worry.
Giediminas won't know anything.
I'm here...
I'm by your side.
What message?
Always...
That his sister need help...
I love you...