This is the year 1325.
It's been 5 years since the coronation of Vladislav I the Elbow-high.
The Polish lands have been reunited under his rule, but the war with the Teutonic Order is still going on.
Silesia and Masovia (Warsaw) are outside Polish borders.
Allies are needed.
For a few years, Elizabeth, the daughter of the Elbow-high and Jadwiga, is the wife of Charles I of Hungary, of the Capetian House of Anjou.
Time has come for the marriage of the only living son of the ruling couple to bear a fruitful alliance...
/praying in Latin/
Oh, Lord...
Bless our Polish kingdom...
Save the king and his subjects from evil...
Amen.
- A strange man...
- I can see...
- This one? Wants to speak with the king only?
- Yes.
Who are you?
Pelka... of Sieciechow...
I'm coming from Lithuania...
I escaped...
from slavery...
Water! Quickly, give him water!
The knight, Pelka of Sieciechow wants to speak to the king.
Pelka? But he's in Lithuanian slavery...
He fled. He's barely alive. He wants to speak with the king.
Bring him here!
My lord, save us!
Do something for those in Gediminas' slavery...
There are so many of us left there...
And nobody will ever mention us...
Winters are heavy...
People die of the cold...
The guards use us as living targets, just for fun.
Shooting at the naked ones with bows.
Their families are too poor to collect the ransom...
But the poor are your subjects too!
There are more and more of them being enslaved...
The border is weak...
Not enough troops...
People live in constant fear...
Let him eat first!
War with Lithuania is out of question.
The Czech king is only waiting for it and he'll move in from the south and he may attack Krakow.
Silesia is already under his control.
Destroying a pagan capital would appeal to the Pope.
Remember about the Teutonic knights, my king.
We attack Lithuania, and they attack us.
Lords, don't leave people without help!
My king, if you want to retain the crown, you have to maintain peace.
Freedom of my subjects is more important than the crown.
This is my father's horse.
- Are you giving it to this man?
I'm following a king's order.
Has my father given Grom to you?
Then you must have done something great.
- So long, my lord!
- Don't you want to rest before your journey?
If you haven't seen home for so long, there's no time to waste.
May God be with you!
A strange man..
Dressed like a peasant, but he mounts a horse like a knight.
That's Pelka. There are not many knights like him anymore. Nothing for himself.
Come on!
Now, think only of the victory, king!
There's only one king in Poland, King Vladislav!
But, one day, you'll be the king.
The crown is heavy, and you need to be watchful lest nobody should topple it.
So?
Lithuanians.
They came at night. The glow was such as if the whole forest was on fire...
And the lady?
Misfortune, my lord.
The lady and the young lords were defending for long
They killed many bastards.
But they got so angry because of their comrades' death
that they were tortured.
Did nobody survive?
Only the young lady.
She hid, but they found her the following day.
Where is she?
The miller's daughter took her to the monastery.
Nobody's managed to baptize Lithuania.
The land is still waiting for the light of Christ.
But such an alliance will give the Teutonic knights the reason for war.
But we'll get a strong all.
Gediminas won't join is in the war with the Teutonic knights.
But he'll release my subjects from slavery.
You heard what Pelka said.
But, isn't there another way? Do we have to ally with pagans?
My queen, in order to acquire these pagans as an ally desperately needed in this situation
and to create new opportunities to convert them to true faith
such an alliance is worth making.
It will only strengthen the Polish crown.
Is that true, Father?
Am I to marry a pagan?
I prefer to go to war.
You'll have your chance to fight.
Mother, have you agreed to this?
Yes.
For the benefit of the subjects and the peace of the kingdom.
You'll marry the daughter of Gediminas, the prince of Lithuania
It has already been decided.
/Lithuanian/ You'll be mine.
/Lithuanian/ For ever.
/Lithuanian/ And only yours.
/Lithuanian/ Your Highness!
/Lithuanian/ Princess
/Lithuanian/ Your father's calling you. I know you're here.
/Lithuanian/ Are you following me?
/Lithuanian/ We're looking for you.
/Lithuanian/ So you tell him you haven't found me.
/Lithuanian/ Don't you know your father?
/Lithuanian/ He'll fly into a rage.
/Lithuanian/ Let's go.
/Lithuanian/ Marry a Pole? I'll never do that!
/Lithuanian/ Watch your tongue! You're speaking to the High Prince!
/Lithuanian/ I'm speaking to my father.
/Lithuanian/ And why don't you want him?
/Lithuanian/ He's not old.
/Lithuanian/ He's a Christian, a stranger.
/Lithuanian/ This is why you'll marry him.
/Lithuanian/ The pope doesn't respect me.
/Lithuanian/ The Teutonic knights murder our people.
/Lithuanian/ You'll become the Polish queen, and, at last, they'll start to respect us.
/Lithuanian/ They're afraid of you.
/Lithuanian/ Isn't it enough for you?
/Lithuanian/ Not enough.
/Lithuanian/ His mother comes from a pious family.
/Lithuanian/ And she'll never agree to a marriage with a...
/Lithuanian/ Pagan!
/Lithuanian/ That's what they call us, isn't it?
/Lithuanian/ They'll baptize you.
/Lithuanian/ Help me, brother!
/Lithuanian/ What have you promised them?
/Lithuanian/ What have you sold me for?
/Lithuanian/ I'll release the Polish prisoners.
/Lithuanian/ What will you gain from this?
/Lithuanian/ I?
/Lithuanian/ There's a lot to say.
/Lithuanian/ I'll be a laughingstock in the east.
/Lithuanian/ Laughingstock among my noblemen.
/Lithuanian/ But you...
/Lithuanian/ You'll be the queen of Poland.
/Lithuanian/ She's in love with another one, Father.
/Lithuanian/ Tough luck.
They're coming.
/Lithuanian/ Have you come for my sister?
/Lithuanian/ We welcome the fiancee of the son of Vladislav, the king of Poland.
/Lithuanian/ Here she is.
/Lithuanian/ Your horses are poor. Weren't there any better in the Wawel Castle stables?
/Lithuanian/ If you ever needed my help
/Lithuanian/ don't hesitate to call me.
/Lithuanian/ I don't want to marry him.
/Lithuanian/ I know.
/Lithuanian/ Stay well, my sister.
We have to go.
It's a long way ahead of us.
And who's that?
/Lithuanian/ Don't you know?
/Lithuanian/ A Lithuanian witch.
/Lithuanian/ Do you remember when you said I was a witch?
/Lithuanian/ Aren't you afraid they'll send me back to Vilnius?
/Lithuanian/ I'm allowed to joke like this. I'm the future queen.
/Lithuanian/ Have you seen your fiancee at last?
Your highness...
Jadwiga, the queen of Poland.
This crucifix is your baptism gift.
Leave us alone.
Leave!
Aldona
From today, never oppose me.
This is my castle.
My kingdom.
In Poland, the king is the ruler, not the queen.
One does not interrupt the queen.
I buried two sons.
I have only Casimirus left.
The future king.
You will have to obey him unconditionally.
Did you understand?
What do you ask the holy church for?
Baptism.
Asking for baptism for a God's child
Aldona, daughter of Gediminas
you're accepting the duty
to bring her up in faith
so that, following God's commandments
she loves God and neighbour
as we were taught by Jesus Christ.
Are you aware of this duty?
We are aware.
Aldona,
do you renounce sin
in order to live in the freedom of the child of God
Do you...
believe in God the Father almighty, creator of heaven and earth
Do you believe?
I believe...
What name have chosen for baptism?
Anna
Anna...
I baptize you
/praying in Latin/
Szczerbiec (the Polish coronation sword)
The sword of the Polish kings. I saw it at your coronation.
Soon it will be yours.
Father, your reign will be long.
And do you want to take the throne?
I will obey you.
I'm asking if...
you want to be the king?
Do you want to rule the country
which is surrounded by peril?
Which was only reunited and immediately everybody's at one another's throat?
Ready to devour one another?
Do you want?
Because it's not easy at all.
I know, I'm learning from you how to rule.
You want to learn?
Remember, you never know who's your enemy.
On the throne, you've got only one ally...
Yourself.
Do you remember what I taught you?
Who's name is God's name, will not be threatened by any danger.
And here...
This sign strengthens the love of kings and princes and the wrath of judges...
Remember, your wife will become a Christian
if she sees you've got an ability for wrath and for love.
Tell everybody at home, you won't be back soon
All of us have got a lot of work at the King's son's wedding.
Princess Anna's cook has arrived.
It's my kitchen.
The queen's order. The woman's staying.
- You understand Polish?
- Better than you Lithuanian.
A pagan or Christian?
And what milk do cows give?
Pagan or Christian?
God, have mercy, only men.
You save thousands of people.
Why didn't you want anything from my father?
You'd rebuild your house, get land.
I'm a knight, not a landowner.
If the knights aren't landowners, there's always war.
Am I to build a house...
And wait in fear for another raid?
I'd rather go to war and serve the king.
Your daughter...
could be my wife's lady-in-waiting.
My lord, she's still a child.
Both are new here.
They may like each other.
She'll have everything here.
Think it over.
Did she tell you she doesn't believe in Jesus?
Whatever she said, I don't believe her.
She received baptism.
She's changed her name, but she hasn't changed her heart.
and that's why I'm worrying about our son.
Our son
is to be the king.
So, first, he has to learn to control his wife
and then Poland.
But he's so young...
He's already a man.
But she doesn't want him.
So he has to
conquer her.
/singing in Latin/
Give your right hands to each other.
I, Casimirus,
the son of Vladislav, the king of Poland
take you, Anna, as wife
and pledge you love,
marital fidelity
to have and to hold
So help me God.