Get up, get up!
What's going on?
Go, wake up my husband!
Tell him to come to my chamber at once!
I came for the payment.
But you haven't done it yet.
I was to deliever it to
the kitchen and I did.
I was to find a man at the
castle and I did. Pay me!
The bells aren't tolling.
That means nobody died.
God takes life away, not me.
Tell your man to do his
job and then I'll pay.
Do you remember the plan?
First, the old woman, then the kids...
and Casimirus, in the end.
He's to see the suffering of his family.
Like we saw the death of the Zachs.
Casimirus is a murderer.
When they start dying, they'll
reinforce the guards.
It will get harder and harder.
You know we can be generous.
You're going to make it!
Algirdas?
You're still here?
Egle...
You were to leave...
Listen to him!
I was on my way...
At the inn behind the forest
we overheard the Hungarians...
They're scheming against you!
Impossible!
They mentioned your name...
Who was that? Names!
Some rich lords, maybe from
your sister's court...
Nonsense!
Are you accusing me of lying?
Are you accusing my sister?
If you died, her husband
would become king of Poland.
Now you'll die! Jasko, sword!
Enough!
- Coward...
- Traitor!
- It's you who betrayed... my sister!
- I'll kill you!
Calm down!
My people are following them
but you have to be careful.
Reinforce the guards.
I'll let Mother know.
So, you can't govern yourself...
Easy, easy!
She should know. You need to warn her too.
I'll let her know.
I'd take Aldona and the kids to Vilnius.
It's safer there.
I can protect my family.
I know. That's why you
should send them with me!
Mum!
Please, think it over.
Bolko will make a better king.
He's a good commander...
He's good with books...
And Casimirus...
Even Elizabeth is tired
of hiding his crimes...
She's been hushing up the Zachs'
case for so many years...
Crown Bolko and the scandals will die away.
Daughter, I don't know why you're
attacking your brother so much...
It's so painful to me.
Why are you doing this?
I'm fighting for my son.
Like you for yours.
Mum I need to talk to you.
Can you leave us alone?
Brother, pray with us
for the father's soul.
Later, Kunegunda.
There's nothing more important
than prayer, is there, mother?
Yes, of course, we'll pray together, but...
now, please, leave us alone for a moment...
Save your soul...
You won't forgive yourself if
anything happens to the kids...
I won't flee...
He's waiting for you...
He hasn't married...
He's at Kestutis's court...
Am I to leave my husband?
An unfaithful husband, a
disrespectful mother-in-law
this strange castle...
I agreed for it 8 years ago...
Casimirus won't hold for long
Almost all his cousins
wander around the Wawel
They pretend they follow the king's will
but they want power for themselves.
Cousins...
Well, but promise me I won't meet him.
You're afraid of yourself...
Get ready.
You're coming home.
I don't believe in the plot.
Maybe they're common travellers.
He came back because of this.
Maybe Algirdas is trying to
set you against your sister.
He's accusing your only
allies of plotting, really?
What if he's right?
How many times have I heard of
plots, magic, poisoned books?
He heard something at the inn
and now he's inspiring panic
I won't let pagans disturb
the king's funeral!
Drink, these herbs can cure...
and soothe nerves...
I'm considering Anna and the
kids hiding somewhere...
Will she agree to that?
Fresh herbs for the queen.
Her highness is fasting, in fact..
And who's that for?
For my lady.
Bring it before it cools.
I feel you're hiding something from me.
I'll keep an eye on you.
You'd better keep an eye
on those who bring this.
The lady complained the food is
not only poor but also cold.
It's a good idea.
Anna should go away.
This way it will be safer.
You said there's no danger.
I don't believe in plots but
the presence of Anna and kids
at the castle poses a problem.
And these Lithuanians...
I can barely stand them.
Mother, please!
Casimirus, don't you understand?
If her brother persuades her to go, use it!
Persuade her it's for her benefit.
Little princesses will be safe, and...
your coronation more peaceful.
My coronation?
Or your crown?
There's only one crown of the queen.
Anna has to wait.
What is it?
To hell with that Polish fasting! Let's go!
First, I'll talk to Casimirus and Jadwiga.
I'll tell them I'll be back for coronation.
I've been waiting for 8 years for that day.
Do you always have to take a risk?
Even with your own life?
I won't give up. Not now.
We have to hurry. My people may be exposed.
Algirdas! You can rely on them, can't you?
Go away! Why have you come here?
Give this coin to daddy.
Ask him to buy something for
you when comes back home.
Thank you, sir.
Tell him I'm waiting for him here,
and I'd like to hear good news.
It's still a child!
You know the way to Wawel, don't you?
I'll be there quick as a flash, sir!
There's not much gold, but the
celebrations must be befitting.
The cook master can spend
as much as he wants.
And is this tomb necessary now?
- Maybe a bit later? - No!
Get the best artist and let him begin.
You summoned us, sire.
Reinforce guards at the gate and the walls.
Pay attention to any strangers.
Are you afraid of something?
I want to be sure the castle is safe.
Cook master! Check all deliveries.
Buy only from trusted merchants.
Yes, your highness.
But her highness, the queen,
already told us to be careful.
I appreciate her thoughtfulness,
but you can't just be careful.
You must be certain the castle is safe.
My family can be scared at the table.
I can vouch for all my people.
And you?
So can I.
Be watchful.
What's going on? Why aren't you at work?
I'm not going back to Wawel. I'm scared.
Scared of what?
- The cook master threatens you. - No.
I saw a strange pouch and two dead rats.
Have you never seen rat poison?
Rat poison in spices?
- Did you tell the cook master? - No!
Why?
Because he wouldn't believe me.
He hates me from the very beginning.
What did you do with this pouch?
Nothing. It disappeared.
So, what are you afraid of?
Because if someone gets
posioned, they'll blame me.
If you run away now, they'll
blame you even more.
You've been serving your
lady for so many years.
- Go back! - No!
You must prove you're
devoted to them and useful.
Not all ends badly.
Vytautas, I'm scared!
Where's she? We'll soon serve the tables.
The woman's not here. It's suspicious.
I'd have to tell the queen about it.
The cook is playing with her guy.
What guy?
She says it's her relative,
but we have our opinion.
Every night she sneaks to the castle town.
Then she always brings
Lituanian delicacies.
But she always lets us try them.
Am I to go to Lithuania?
I'll show you my country at last.
You know my father was in slavery there.
- Are you afraid of me? - Not you, but...
Easy, you're safe with us.
Trust us.
What's on?
Cudka's afraid to go to Lithuania.
And you believe her?
She wants to stay here for Casimirus...
Women! You're blind.
Don't kill. Forgive me.
What happened?
The Hungarians disappeared!
How disappeared? Where did they go?
I don't know. We fell asleep.
Get out.
They didn't talk about anything important.
And their strange language...
So, we fell asleep.
Out!
Out of my sight!
And what now?
Now, everyone at the
castle may be your enemy.
Sire...
Is Anna ready for the feast?
I beg you, don't tell
us to go to Lithuania.
Let me stay here, I don't want to leave.
It's not going to be for long.
Are you in danger?
I'm not afraid of myself, but you all.
You shouldn't stay alone.
So many guests and so much work!
Where have you been?
Forgive me, sir!
I've got to tell you something.
Speak!
There was a pouch on the shelf.
With white powder.
And two dead rats next to it.
I went to throw them away.
When I was back, the pouch disappeared.
Don't look at me like this.
And what did you do?
I scrubbed the shelf clean
in case it was some rat poison,
so that nobody gets hurt.
I knew it! I knew you're
hiding something from me!
I didn't do anything!
Why didn't you tell me?
Would you believe me?
What was I to do? I
didn't know who to tell?
Guards!
None of your cooks would even notice
if something was added to the food.
You should have told me!
You should have told me you saw it!
Guards!
Are you going to scare me with guards?
Why do you think I'm back?
Because I feel sorry for the kids.
I feel sorry for my lady... and you.
There is a poisoner at the castle.
Maybe even in our kitchen.
What will you get from putting me to jail?
What's going on?
There are strangers wandering
in the cloisters...
I'm innocent, I swear...
I'd like to believe you.
Give stronger beers.
Two at each entry. King's order.
Nobody goes home for the night.
My family's waiting for me.
They can wait!
This is service!
Don't drink from the king's table!
More!
You see, I'm not so scary...
To hell with you!
Did you find your father? Did
you tell him what to do?
I couldn't find him. I walked
around the whole castle.
Not good. You promised me.
And where's the coin I gave you?
You're not lying?
Did you go to the castle?
Not your fault. Keep it.
Thank you.
I'll have to wait for your husband, then.
He was to do something for me.
I need to be sure he didn't disappoint me.
Maybe you clean this place?!
I'll go get water.
You're not going anywhere.
You've come here to mourn Vladislav.
But also to welcome the new king.
We have bonds of blood and faith.
That's why I ask, let's pray...
for our unity and good fortune.
/praying in Latin/
So, who are we welcoming on the
throne, Casimirus or Bolko?
Isn't there a better candidate?
No, there isn't.
Stop it! Enough!
I heard it. Aren't you ashamed?
The king's dead body is
still in his chamber
and you're already questioning his will.
Well, we want to talk about this will.
Bolko, I ask you for gtreater
respect for Casimirus.
Do you think one victorious
battle makes you a king?
Yes.
I defeated the Czechs.
I'm changing my duchy.
And Casimirus?
Is he changing anything except his bedroom?
Eat those words!
Eat those words or I'll kill you.
Kill him!
Stop it!
Humiliation is a worse punishment.
Stop, please.
Kunedgunda, please, you should
apologize to your brother.
I'm not going to, mum.
You don't need to apologize me.
Enough of these whispers in the shadows.
Let's meet tomorrow and speak frankly.
If anybody questions my crown, be brave
to tell me that straight in the face.
Jasko, tomorrow you summon Spytek,
the chancellor and the archdeacon.
Everybody has to be present.
My beloved daughter-in-law is
leaving us, unfortunately.
She's leaving with prince Algirdas.
So, let's drink for their safe journey.
Lady, I'm grateful, but
I decided not to go.
Forgive me, Algirdas, but I
can't accept your invitation.
My place is here, with my husband.
The future king of Poland.
My husband will kill you
if he sees you here.
He probably prefers to make some profit.
Who are you and what do you want?
The same as him.
The death of the king and his family.