Forgive me that I distract you from your vigil
at the Lord's tomb, but it's important.
Can I tell you everything, Brother?
You confess to God, not human.
And will you keep the secret?
We swear it when we become priests,
so you don't need to worry, lady.
I'm not worthy celebrating
the Resurrection.
I'm not as pious as queen Jadwiga,
I can't pray like this.
Is that what you wanted to confess to me?
I keep asking God to help
me forget something.
I follow the commandments,
but I can't help my memory
- I can't...
- Entrust your worry to Christ.
He'll certainly help you.
I burned souvenirs of my past life,
and it didn't help.
After so many years, I can't
forget my first beloved one.
The more I try,
The more often I reminisce about him.
It's a sin, isn't it?
Don't fear.
Never compare yourself to others.
You don't think those gathered in
the chapel are without sin, do you?
Christ suffers for all of us.
And he waits for all of us.
If only Martin could see this...
Rose, people are gathering
at Christ's tomb. Come!
Look, his head keeps dropping.
Like Harcik when he got drunk.
And then he beat you. Come.
That's the way he was.
At least I wasn't all alone.
When we're all, you can't be alone, come.
Do you think he's in paradise?
For sure, come, Rose.
/singing in Latin/
/praying in Latin/
Egle?
What silence at the castle!
Even the guards let me in without trouble.
I've got the amulet you asked for.
Here's your pay.
- You'd better not show it to anybody.
- Thank you.
I'll beg our gods to help my lady.
What's the problem?
She's got to choose which gods to trust.
That's none of my business.
Do you think they really believe
you can die and then resurrect?
I don't know. But they
do want to believe it.
I'll never comprehend it.
I'll go to town. People are leaving church.
Maybe I'll do some business?
To town or to the kitchen?
/singing in Polish/
Have you brought anything?
Dried in the sun for half a
year, and rubbed with herbs.
So dried or rubbed?
Interchangeably. In Poland, you have
no idea what a good sausage is.
Where's Gabia?
I'va got a Lithuanian pirog for her.
With groats and cheese.
She's just gone out with a Hungarian cook.
Where?
To church.
Have you got more of this kindziukas?
We've got Lithuanian visitors. Do
you want to make a profit or not?
I'll unpack everything in a moment.
But don't touch the pirog
and this one either.
That's for my little cook.
Little cook...
Mother, guests are waiting.
We'll see the soon, but the
matters is very urgent.
Sit down, please.
I don't believe in your wife's conversion.
I looked at her during the prayer.
Don't defend her. It's not necessary.
Mother...
It's a holy day today. Very important.
Christ's resurected. We should rejoice!
I'm rejoicing. I only
wanted to help you both.
I want to help Anna. She's been
with us for so many years.
She watches our ceremonies but
she doesn't participate in them.
And, I guess, you've got a plan.
No... I've got no plan.
You should have one.
Your wife won't be peaceful as long as Lithuanians
practice their sorcery at the castle.
- What sorcery?
- Don't pretend you don't know.
They all do this. Some
grains, grain-ears...
Nobody will go through the door
because the smoke suddenly changed...
- This is a task for you. - For me?
So, am I to throw them away?
These people are dear to my wife.
I believe you'll find a way to help them.
Start with Anna.
When she was baptized, she was very young.
Now she should understand more.
Fine, but I'm not a priest.
Priests are responsible
for spiritual matters,
and you are responsible for...
matters of all kinds.
The Lithuanians are here to stay,
and it depends on you whether
they'll respect our god
and our customs.
This is the king's role.
And for such a king shall you be annoited.
Now, let's go. The guests are waiting.
They must be hungry.
And so am I.
Let's go, son.
/humming/
Finish with these peppers.
Peppers, peppers with everything!
Good peppers.
Put this meat in a pot
and fill it with water.
I'll do it. He's never made broth.
So, teach him!
Maybe there will be some use of him.
He sings beautifully.
In Hungariarn...
A nice man.
The cook should cook.
Maybe you show us what
you can do, will you?
Peppers, peppers...
/speaking Hungarian/
Very good.
Let him go back to his place.
Such a nice man.
Nice?
Everything will be fine.
After Lent, whatever we put
on the table will be eaten.
Egle, I told you we don't
need these things here.
Gods aren't angry with you,
but don't offend them.
- Say goodbye to them. - No.
I know you mean well.
You're lost, lady. The father's and the
local beliefs struggle inside your soul.
No wonder you can't find your place.
But be careful.
You'll lose yourself and
you won't be happy.
This is not your country
and not your faith.
This is my country, Egle.
Here is my home, my
husband and my children.
Can't you see it?
You've been here with
me for such a long time
and you still haven't learned?
Here everybody's watching and judging.
Egle, if I don't show them I believe,
they won't believe me.
Is this what you want, really?
Do you want to be like them?
You never will.
You want to convert. So be it.
But be yourself. Giediminas's daughter.
Holy Mary!
Is this how you greet me, cousin?
Whenever I see you I
recall my Martin's pain...
Stop blaming me. I didn't do anything
to him, and I'm in trouble myself.
He was my first runaway.
You could have spoken out for
him, and you did nothing.
The executor must do his duty.
Martin has never been good to you.
Your parents told you this.
And you were stubbornly in love.
He drank, beat you, didn't love or care...
He wanted to push the blame on you,
as if you gave him this poison.
I said it before, so I don't
need to waste my time.
What have you got?
It's expired. And you said you
bought it from the Hungarians.
It's for sale, not for you.
It's a holy day today. You'd
give us a cup or two?
Where's Casimirus?
I can't see the children.
Shouldn't they be at the table?
You'll see, Mother. Hungarian vegetable
stew is the best for children's pale skin.
I'll make sure little Elizabeth tries it.
Isn't the music too loud?
Maybe we tell them to stop playing?
Archdeacon!
Is it true God doesn't like
music during the meal?
I haven't asked.
Lord, bless thy gifts which
we are about to receive.
Amen.
A gift from Charles. The
best of Hungarian vineyards.
Dear guests.
I'd like to request so
much that I lack words.
But while requesting,
I'd like to thank you,
although I can't mention everyone,
for advice, support, mediation,
or for spiritual care which
we've been given recently.
I'd like to thank most and reward
with three villages in Greater Poland
our archdeacon of Krakow,
Jaroslaw Bogoria of Skotniki.
It's very generous, sire, but there maybe
more urgent matters from more needy subjects.
Power with no money must
cultivate alliances.
What did you say?
Pope John teaches that the
rich don't need allies.
And the poor must buy them all the time.
Elaborate, excellency.
So said my father, who, as you know, is
quite close to the head of our church.
Excellency, try a Lithuanian
dish, your allies' cuisine.
It won't hurt scholarly disputes.
Good you've come.
You need to rejoice together
on a day like this.
Here...
Lord has resurrected!
Wouldn't you find some warm food for
travellers robbed by bandits on the road?
- Where?
Around half a day from the turnpike.
Near a wood with young lindens.
What bandits rob Christians on a holy day?
There's bread and beer for the child.
Fresh home brew, warm soup, should I serve?
- God bless you for your good heart.
- Amen.
I'd better go to watch the stall.
Easy, the bandits were on the road.
There are guards in town.
I've got a premonition...
Rose, wait. I'll go with you.
So long!
Cudka, dance with us, please!
Nobody's dancing. We're mourning.
We want to dance, please!
- So dance! - We want to dance with you!
Lady! Can I dance with the girls?
Grandma, please!
This is the best babka (cake but also
woman in Polish) in our kitchen.
I prefer bread with cheese.
With cheese? Then I prefer our pirog.
So, you've prepared this wonder of yours!
Peppers!
Let me see!
Beer!
Milk! Milk!
Water!
So, didn't I say he'll kill us all here?
/speaking Hungarian/ Peppers...
Hot?
Hot!
Damn it!
Cudka!
Time to take the kids!
But we want to stay!
Take them with Helen.
Girls, to the chambers, please.
But you will join us later, won't you?
Maybe it's time for us as well?
Lent has finished not only on the table.
Holy Mary! They plundered the whole house.
Nothing! Nothing's left!
All there's left to do is to
jump into the river like Martin.
Rose!
King Vladislav died, and what did I say?
There were no bandits under his rule!
There were but only on roads!
There weren't.
As if I wasn't miserable enough...
It's better to drown at once
and the suffering is over.
Where's Cudka?
She went to dance, but I'm here.
Bring me some Tokaji, then.
Give me a son!
Egle...
Hide it.
She only cares.
I know but only God protects you.
There's no need for trinkets.
I'll throw them away.
Throw them from your
heart, most importantly...