Drink, daughter.
Who did it?
Who wanted to poison you, mum?
We'll get to know.
Now, I'm worried about you.
Drink.
I want to go home. To my place.
Take a rest first.
I only fainted.
They wanted to poison you.
Go with me to Sachsen.
You shouldn't stay here after all that happened.
You're sweet.
Mum, you care so much so that your mother is beatified.
We'll take care of this.
I'll ask Rudolf.
He'll arrange your meeting with the pope.
But Casimirus can't be left alone now.
I can't leave him.
He'll manage on his own.
Yes, I'm praying for this,
but I can't leave now.
Not now.
It's not only about Casimirus, is it?
We've been attacked and
I need to make sure the traitors are punished.
It's really Casimirus's fault.
Everybody's saying it's the Zachs' revenge.
I don't believe it.
How long will you defend him?
Be calm and prudent. Don't let them provoke you.
I won't touch the envoy, but I won't forgive them the latest war.
The father died because of the Teutonic knights.
You yourself wanted to negotiate with them.
Be careful, they know the country is weakened by wars,
they know we have no troops,
let's face it, we don't pose any threat to them.
At least, don't let them know your intentions
If they're not afraid of us, at least make them afraid of yourself.
What would Father say about this?
Be the king, at last, and not just the king's son!
Ask the Teutonic envoy in!
He caused so much evil and misery!
Don't indulge him so much.
Kunegunda, what are you saying?
Everybody's afraid to tell you this.
Casimirus isn't fit to be the king.
People laugh at him.
Ha can only land our family in trouble.
Like with Clara Zach in Hungary...
I don't believe Hungarians wanted to poison me.
And if it is Anna?
Mum!
She came to the table later than anybody...
It's her brother who warned Casimirus.
Don't be blinded by your hatred of her.
No, no, darling.
Algirdas tried to confuse us.
He spread rumours of Hungarian conspiracy.
I don't believe it.
They want to get rid of me, so that Anna becomes queen.
Do you really believe they would do that?
This is the position of Great Teutonic Master,
Lothar von Braunschweig.
We also want a truce.
You should reconsider the alliance with Lithuania.
The pope condemned your deal with pagans.
The order has a mission.
We bring the light of Christ.
Mainly with sword...
Let's talk about salvation,
not about its tools.
An alliance with us against Giediminas would give you more profits.
That's not possible.
You highness knows the first commandment.
I know it well. My wife is a Christian.
Lithuanians are and will be our allies.
I'm only warning.
If you attack Christian states together,
there may be a crusade against Krakow.
Nobody wants it.
Spytek, you'll go to Torun.
What shall I tell the Great Master?
We'll sign the truce...
on hitherto terms.
Have them cleaned before the funeral.
I did what you told me. Free my family.
That's all you can get for the cup-bearer.
It must be the king or queen, not some courtier.
I don't want money, but to know if they're alive.
Let me go!
You agreed. You wanted to make a profit.
Go back to your service.
We're waiting at the inn by the forest.
I beg you, don't hurt my children.
You're risking their lives with every moment.
You're to be at the inn at angelus,
with information for whom the bells are tolling.
Don't try to lie to us anymore.
Your son can say prayers so beautifully.
It would be a pity if he died.
Look mum, we shared with Yolanta.
I'm happy you've got good hearts.
That's what most important in life.
Grandma says ten commandments are most important.
They're very important
but so are good deeds.
You've never spoken to them like this, what's on?
Their lives are in your hands. Keep an eye on them.
You don't need to worry.
They haven't found the traitors who wanted to poison my mother-in-law.
Nobody knows who else they may hurt.
So, the princesses aren't going to the funeral ceremony?
No, and they must stay here until I'm back.
Nobody can enter this room.
I can trust only you.
Watch my children.
And Egle, please, no more stories about dragons.
Take it, please.
- Money.
- This is the queen's decision.
Your husband saved her life.
Money won't bring him back.
If you want land, a village, say it.
Sire, forgive me, but I have a request...
You'll get what you want.
I don't want money but I have a request, a great one...
Accept my son, Nicholas, to the service at your court...
He's a good boy and he'l be useful to you.
Send him here right after the funeral.
Chancellor, take care of him.
Good bye, lady.
You doubted, sire.
There may be trouble with him.
Gather everyone in the hall and let them say last goodbye to the king.
Has the one in the vault said anything?
Have we got any lead?
He only brought the poison in.
Hang him right after the funeral.
Why aren't your daughters here?
Children need to be accustomed to death.
So that they don't fear it.
They'd better remember the king as he was alive.
He's alive!
His life will be eternal.
Father...
King Vladislav!
What are we to do?
Help your mother.
Why isn't he here?
Father!
Martin!
I brought you bread.
I don't want to eat.
I want to leave this place.
Help me.
What can I do?
You need to find the hooded one.
The one who paid me.
Too late.
You admitted that you brought the poison.
I didn't know what I was carrying.
Did the money eclipse your mind?
The hooded one took me in. He said it was spice.
And now I have to rot in a vault... with rats.
- That's my husb... - Quiet, I know!
You said something about a hooded man, who is it?
I don't know, a stranger. I never saw him before.
Where can I find him?
How can I know?
He comes out of nowhere, Hungarians pay him.
And who poured the poison, him?
No, he didn't enter Wawel. The guard, Roch, didn't let him in.
He lives in Stradom. The hooded one talked to Roch only.
Why didn't Roch let him in? The gates were open.
How can I know? I'm not the guard of guards.
Take it.
Do something, stupid!
You're scolding me again!
Rot here!
I'll be better off without you.
My love!
Come back!
Stay.
Keep looking for the traitor.
You'd like to have your own kids, wouldn't you?
With Niemierza...
I hardly know him.
He's always on a mission...
And you?
You'd like to get married, would you?
You like Jasko, don't you?
My father will never let me marry him.
Why? He's near the king.
He's from Tarnow.
So what?
I'm from Greater Poland, from Poznan.
Don't you understand?
Our families will never let us be together.
Can't you beg your father?
You don't know him...
He's different from yours.
Tell us about this love!
Sure.
This story is called itolorauda.
The lady told us not to open to anybody.
Egle?
Check who's there.
But don't let anybody in.
Are you Roch?
No, sire. I'm Macko.
Where is he?
He finished his watch and left.
Have you seen Roch?
He went to see off the king.
The cook master sent this for the girls.
I can't let anybody in.
But they must be thirsty. I was to bring it to them.
The girl was to bring it.
They're preparing lunch.
There's nobody left for errands.
Is it for kids? They're thirsty.
We're allowed to take it only from the girl cook.
Or the table master.
I want to drink!
Back to the room! You can't go out.
Cudka, hide the kids!
God forgive me!
My family...
Somewhere behind the inn... in the forest!
They got them... Save... my family...
Have you heard, prince?
The inn in the forest!
Somebody kidnapped his family. He begged to free them!
Lock the door! Hide the kids!
Treason! Follow me, quickly!
I'll explain on the way.
Queen Jadwiga forbids putting dragon's tongues on the table, chancellor!
Had they been here yesterday, Jan would be alive now.
Her highness says prayer is stronger.
Tell that to his widow. She was here to collect his body.
She asked the king to accept Nichloas for service at the court.
Holy Christ, not him!
Why?
I haven't met anybody weirder than him.
There will be only trouble with him.
The king has promised.
There's no other way.
I've asked so many times not to put this when I'm here.
Your highness, it was the chancellor's order.
He's still upset with having exposed you to danger yesterday.
The prayer's enough.
God will protect us then.
Your highness, everybody believes dragon's tongues protect from poison,
so why not?
God shouldn't mind.
How do you know what God minds?
This is superstition.
Do you remember how the father was proud of them?
I ordered to take them from the treasury, here...
They don't disturb the prayer, do they?
But they may do harm to salvation.
Poison in the castle. They wanted to kill the girls.
God, only the Lithuanians stayed at the castle.
Algirdas, Egle!
Go to the forest and kill them. We don't need them.
First, the payment.
Bring the proof the job's done.
What do you want me to bring you?
The crown of kings?
Bells aren't tolling.
People aren't talking.
So nobody died at the castle.
I did my job.
The money pouch.
My daughters.
Yolanta, come to me.
Come, don't worry.
Michal and Rafal, follow me.
Stay with them.
Take them alive!
We need to deliver them alive!
Kill me, but tell me Casimirus is dead.
Are you a Zach?
It's impossible, all of them are dead!
Speak!
Go to hell, pagan scum!
Clara didn't deserve to die.
And your king doesn't deserve to live.
Where's your man in the hood?
Speak!
You'll never find him.
The Zachs' revenge will reach you.