(orchestral music)
(upbeat rock music)
(upbeat rock music continues)
(audience applauding)
(audience applauding continues)
- Hello, welcome to "Top Gear."
We're back from our World Cup break.
And, to be honest,
we've found ourselves in
a little bit of a pickle.
- See, the thing is,
we have to record this week's
episode way in advance.
So we've got no idea who's won.
- Not a clue.
So we're gonna read you our bets.
First, let's go with the favourites.
Congratulations, Brazil.
Well done.
(audience applauding)
You've got it again.
(Freddie laughing)
Who else?
- Congratulations, Germany.
(audience booing and laughing)
- Ooh.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
- Too soon?
Presume penalties?
(Freddie and Chris laughing)
- And I guess, everyone,
there's always a chance.
It might have happened.
England!
(audience cheering)
- It's not, is it?
- It's not, it's not.
- It is not.
- Lads, don't forget Wales.
- What?
- Don't forget Wales.
- Let's not go mad.
(audience laughing)
Right, what we do know is,
it's our last episode of the
series and it's a belter.
Later on, we're gonna give you
some useful curb-buying advice,
but we kick off with the
best noise in the world.
(gentle music)
(engine zooming)
(gentle music continues)
(engine roaring)
That is the sound of a Ferrari V12.
(exhales) That is the sound of Italy.
And what sound it is.
(engine roaring)
A sound that lives in the heart
of the Daytona SP3.
(engine roaring)
Oh, come on.
(rock music)
Born out of the Prancing
Horse's special project stable,
Maranello's latest cost
1.8 million pounds.
And its only purpose in life
is to celebrate this glorious
marque's glorious history.
The V12 is Ferrari.
The first ever road car
they built some 75 years ago
was powered by a V12,
and they've been building them ever since.
This one is the most powerful of the lot.
829 horsepower.
Don't mind if I do.
(engine roaring)
(intense orchestral music)
Whoa, whoa.
Listen to that.
As celebrations go, that is a good start.
(gentle music)
But where the real surprise comes
is in the way they've
put this car together.
There are no turbos,
batteries, or e-motors here.
No four-wheel drive, either.
Nor even the usual floppy
bits of active aero.
No, the Daytona is unusually old school.
(engine zooming)
(light orchestral music)
This is Ferrari getting
a little bit nostalgic,
which, to be honest, isn't very Ferrari.
They're all about the
future and advancement
and developing the next bit of tech.
But just this once,
they've took a little
trip down memory lane.
Sure, 0 to 60 in less than three seconds,
and a 211-mile-an-hour top speed
are all very modern numbers.
Dear me.
But the attitude of the car
is much more old-fashioned.
The steering is a little bit weightier
than the usual Ferrari
and they've engineered a bit
of a thump on the gear change,
but it gives it a real old school feel.
And check this out for retro.
Pop-up headlights.
(Paddy chuckles)
I mean, it's close enough, isn't it?
Come on.
(engine zooming)
And as for the rest of
the way the Daytona looks,
that all comes from Ferrari's deep dive
into the old family albums.
(sweeping orchestral music)
First, you've got that
futuristic slatted tail,
borrowed from the 250 P5 concept of 1968.
The bulging wings with those
side mirrors pushed on top,
a pure historic endurance racer.
In fact, the name, basic shape,
even bits of the interior,
all lead back to the
legendary P330 series cars
that, back in 1967, took
a one, two, three finish
at the 24 Hours of Daytona.
And look at that view over the bonnet.
It makes you feel like
a proper racing driver
from back in the day.
Pop on a crash helmet, a pair of overalls,
couple of laps of Italy,
then back home to England
for tea and crumpets.
(engine roaring)
But while there's no denying
the sense of occasion
the Daytona's stripped-back
retro racer vibes deliver,
in a couple of places,
they might have taken it a bit too far.
For starters, take these seats.
Now when you buy a Daytona,
Ferrari measure you up
and then glue some cushions to the chassis
in the exact right position.
But what happens if your
partner or your mates
doesn't have the exact
same size hips as you?
It's gonna be a very uncomfortable ride.
And then we've got the carbon fibre roof.
Once that's off, it's off.
So if the weather turns
and it starts to rain,
you're gonna get wet,
unless you pop this on,
which isn't very Ferrari.
It's more like you're
going on a camping trip.
Doesn't scream 1.8 million quid, does it?
If we're being honest, though,
none of that actually matters.
(light piano music)
The Daytona's not meant to be practical
in the same way it's not
meant to be the fastest
or the most cutting-edge supercar going.
Really, the best way to think of it
is as a 1.8-million-pound work of art.
It's a portal to another time.
It makes people smile.
And it certainly makes me smile.
(Paddy laughs)
(engine roaring)
But like so many works of art,
the real sadness is that most people
will never get to experience the Daytona.
The 600-odd that Ferrari's building
will all be locked away in
climate-controlled garages,
doomed to be passed
around the 0.1-percenters
as nothing more than investments.
And that is an absolute travesty.
So while I've still got the Daytona
for another couple of hours,
it's time to give a little bit back.
It's time to let the people enjoy it.
(folk music)
Oh, yes.
You can forget UberLUX.
It's time to say ciao to Pad's Cabs.
(sighs) Let's wait for a fare now.
Ciao, ciao.
Hello, yes, grazie.
Well, could be my first
bit of business here.
- Ciao.
Taxi?
- Grazie.
- In you come, there you go.
Ferrari Daytona.
- Wow.
(engine purrs)
Okay, you ready?
- Ready.
Wow, wow!
(engine roaring)
- Ooh. (laughs)
(Paddy and passenger laughing)
- Ooh, a man of the cloth.
- Taxi?
- Si, Father.
In, get in.
- Grazie.
- Buongiorno.
- Here we go.
(engine roaring)
(Paddy laughs)
So that's two happy
customers up and running.
- Wow.
- I love Ferrari.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Ah.
- The third, though...
Taxi?
(passenger speaking in Italian)
- [Paddy] Will take a
bit more winning over.
It's a bit of a squeeze to get in.
Ah, way.
Whoa. (chuckles)
(passenger speaking in Italian)
- Shall we?
- Si, si, si, si, si.
- Oh, god, that's not gonna...
That's not...
That's not gonna work.
(passenger sighs)
All right.
Like all supercars, boot space
in the Daytona is an issue.
(passenger speaking in Italian)
But no nonna can resist the Ferrari V12.
(engine purrs)
Ooh.
(passenger speaking in Italian)
- Exactly.
Hold on tight.
(engine roaring)
- Ah!
(passenger speaking in Italian)
(Paddy chuckling)
- But then, of course,
driving a cab through
a town you don't know,
in a country whose
language you don't speak,
does present a few more challenges.
Um, (speaks in Italian).
(passenger speaking in Italian)
- Uh...
- The market.
- Market, si.
Directionie?
- Piazza Duomo.
- Piazza?
- Duomo.
- Duomo. (chuckles)
(Father speaking in Italian)
- San Bernadino, okay.
Sono Paddy.
- Paddy?
- Paddy.
Sono Paddy.
Name, my name.
- Oh.
- Father, Paddy.
My Italian's coming on a treat.
This is kind of the point of it all,
because with the Daytona,
it really doesn't matter
where you're going.
This car makes any
journey properly special.
This car?
- Si.
- [Paddy] 2 million euros.
- Woo.
- Ooh.
- Oh.
very expense.
- Oh, very. (whistles)
- Too much for common people.
- Too much, too much.
(Paddy and passenger laughing)
0 to 60 miles per hour in
less than three seconds.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
(engine roaring)
- Wow.
Wow.
Ah! (giggling)
- Whoa. (laughing)
- It's so crazy. (laughing)
- [Paddy] It's quick.
- It's a crazy taxi.
- Yeah, it is a crazy taxi, yeah.
(jazzy music)
And this crazy taxi
gets a five-star rating.
- To be in a Ferrari, it's a lovely dream.
- It is beautiful.
- Good to hear.
- I love so much this car.
I fall in love with this car.
- Yeah, I love this car as well.
And here we go.
Fantastic.
- Oh, oh.
- Car seat, here we go.
That's the one.
Oh, watch your head, watch your head.
There we go.
You got everything?
Oh, uh, basket, shopping.
(passenger speaking in Italian)
- Si, two minutes.
Okay, here we go.
(engine roaring)
(Paddy speaking in Italian)
(sweeping orchestral music)
There we go.
Thank you very much.
- Thank you so much.
- Oh, lovely.
- Bye-bye, thank you.
- Bye-bye, bye-bye.
(engine roaring)
(Father speaking in Italian)
- It's okay?
- Grazie, grazie.
Thank you, Father, thank you.
So the good people of L'Aquila
have experienced the joy of the Daytona.
Here we go.
- Grazie, grazie, grazie.
Grazie.
(uplifting orchestral music)
And now, there's just one job left to do.
And that's to take this work of art
back to its climate-controlled garage
300 miles away.
Avanti.
(audience applauding)
- That's a lovely car.
- It's nice, that one.
- Ooh.
- Come on, I'm jealous.
- What a Ferrari.
- Jealous, jealous.
- Beautiful car.
Beautiful car.
And honestly, the attention
it got was unbelievable.
- But do you think the looks are enhanced
by the plastic taxi triangle
that you slapped to the roof?
(audience laughing)
- That's just the cherry
on top of the cake, Chris.
And let me tell you, Pads
Cabs did a roaring trade.
You might not arrive with your luggage,
but you'll get there very, very quickly.
(audience laughing)
- Well, Paddy, 1.8 million quid.
I don't think cabbies
are gonna be going out
ditching the Priuses just yet.
- No, no, it is bonkers money,
but, listen, everything's
bonkers money these days.
Look at the price of a pint in London.
He knows, he'll tell you.
(audience laughing)
You need a drink after you've
paid for one, mate, don't you?
(audience laughing)
You're right,
but there's still one vehicle
that's doing a booming trade.
And that's the humble van.
Because thanks to the flourishing business
of online deliveries,
it's all happening in the
world of vans right now.
You want a new one?
You spoiled for choice.
What have we got, lads?
- I love this, the ID. Buzz Cargo.
The van version of the
new electric VW love bus.
I'll admit it.
Not the cheapest, not the biggest.
But look at it, it's far more interesting
than a boring diesel box.
- Lovely looking thing, yeah.
- Crystals, what about you?
- Mercedes eVito.
Again, all electric, 160 miles of range.
Much, much clever inside
than your average white van.
- Yeah.
And we've got, everyone,
a Ford Transit Custom.
- There she is.
- Come on, enjoy it.
(audience applauding)
Last year, this was the
best-selling vehicle in the UK.
Not the best-selling van,
the best-selling vehicle.
It outsold Fiestas, Focuses,
Corsairs, Golfs, the lot.
Amazing.
- But here's the issue,
because a shiny van like
this doesn't come cheap.
Apparently, this one, 41 grand.
- [Audience] Ooh.
- I know, I know it is crazy,
but what if you want to
get into the delivery game
on a budget?
- Well, to find out,
the producers gave us each three grand
and told us to buy ourselves a van,
give it a proper delivery
company paint job,
and prepare for some challenges.
(suspenseful music)
At the risk of making this piece
of consumer testing rather brief,
getting into the delivery
game on a budget is simple.
When it comes to vans, you
can't beat the original.
The best, the Ford Transit.
Not only British-built, but
pretty much built Britain.
(elegant orchestral music)
It's part of the fabric of our nation.
And I've got myself a minter
here, just 230,000 miles.
It's barely run in.
If you're going to deliver stuff,
I don't know why you'd
deliver in anything else.
- [Freddie] Unless, that is,
you want it delivered faster.
(rock music)
- Yeah, I really don't why
you'd choose anything...
A sprightly entry?
- Hello.
- First of all, Fred-
- What?
- No notes on the name.
Absolutely superb, bang on.
- Smashed it, I know.
- You have.
- Smashed it.
- I can't complain.
That's superb.
One question.
The brief said, "Buy a van."
You bought a family estate
car with no windows.
- This is an Astravan.
In the cities, you wanna
be fast, get your parcels,
you wanna be nimble,
you wanna park it easy.
This does all that and looks great.
- Okay, let's talk performance.
Engine?
- It's a 1.9.
- Yep.
- Diesel.
- Yeah, cool.
- [Freddie] I got some new rims.
I've got a spoiler on the back.
It looks the part, Chris.
- Scenario.
- Yeah.
- Hi, FredEX, I want to
deliver a sofa, please.
- Yes, I will sort that out.
Then I'll put the phone down.
- Yep.
- Hi, Chris.
I hear you've got a Transit
van down at Purple Sector.
(Chris and Freddie laughing)
Could you deliver a couch for me?
I started speaking and then
I saw the name. (laughing)
The Purple Sector.
- Let me talk you through
Purple Sector Delivery, okay?
- Yeah.
- If you want fast, accurate deliveries,
Purple Sector is all about motorsport.
'Cause when you go quickest
in a sector on a racetrack,
you go purple.
This is about speed.
This is about being the quickest.
- Speed?
It's a Transit van.
This is about speed.
- I reckon, in a straight
line, that would toast that.
- Shut up.
- It would.
- A Transit van?
- It's a winner.
Come on, it's a winner.
- So are are you gonna be
the quintessential Transit van driver?
- I'm an aggressive little
man in a Transit van.
- Wow.
(upbeat music)
- [Paddy] Come on.
Do you want those cowboys
knocking at your door?
Would you prefer a more reliable service?
- [Chris] Oh my lord.
- I can't wait for this.
Come on then.
(Freddie chuckling)
- Good morning, gentlemen.
- Good morning.
- How are we?
- Is it Postman Pat or Postman Pad?
- I'm going back to an era
when the postal service was respected.
(Freddie chuckling)
You two look like you've come
off the set of "SeaBabies."
- What? (laughs)
- Coming from you? (laughs)
- Right, there's a lot
to take in here, Pad.
First of all-
- Do start, Chris.
- The choice of van, VW Caddy.
Paddy in a Caddy.
- Based on the old Volkswagen
Golf, handles fantastically.
700 kilos in the back.
Look at it.
It's a beauty.
Don't it not make you smile,
a bright red van like that?
- You got one thing missing, though.
- What?
- Where's Jess?
- Wait.
- Where's Jess? (chuckles)
- He's not-
- I don't wanna know.
- He's not got a cat in the back of it.
- [Paddy] Here she is.
(Freddie laughing)
- [Chris] Okay, that's not acceptable.
- [Freddie] There's nothing
right about that. (laughs)
- Who said, officially?
- No, it can't. (laughs)
Now it's just staring at me.
It's just not
a real cat, is it.
- I can't deal with this.
- Careful.
- Is it a real cat?
- She's a bit funny with strangers.
- No, that was someone's pet.
- Still is, it's mine.
(Chris and Freddie laughing)
- [Chris] So this day had
gone weird unusually quickly.
But nevertheless, we'd
been told it was time
to put our delivery vans to the test
at a nearby mystery location.
A mystery location happily
located somewhere beyond the end
of this runway.
- [Paddy] Go on, Purple
Member, start us off.
- Purple Sector.
- Sorry.
- Three, two, one, go.
(brakes screeching)
(upbeat rock music)
- Oh, boy, I'm the Astravan man.
- Oh, look at this.
I'm being taken down by the Astra.
- Ooh.
- Oh, look at it.
And the bloody Paddy as well.
Oh.
(upbeat rock music)
I'm getting hammered here.
- I already said it was gonna happen here.
This is the future of deliveries.
- I was quietly confident
that the rear-wheel drive,
very lightweight, empty Transit
van would do quite well,
but I was absolutely thumped there.
(upbeat rock music)
- Exactly.
In the world of deliveries,
most of the time, it's
not size that's important.
It's speed.
All these huge delivery
vans tooling around town,
if you look at them,
they're never full of stuff.
You know, people order socks,
charging cables, small things.
This is all you need, one of these.
Won't delay in this, I'll be there early.
I'm bringing a bit of
sportiness to the van world.
- Now this particular
generation of Transit
was one of the last to be built in the UK.
And being a Ford,
it actually drives a lot
better than it needs to.
The steering's good, the brakes are good,
the gearshift is fine.
And I tell you what, it is fun to drive.
(upbeat rock music)
And when you're spending
your whole working week behind the wheel,
that is frankly much more important
than where you put your stuffed cat.
- You cool enough, my love?
You know, there's something lovely
about seeing a bright red
van coming down the road.
That little nod back to
happy, innocent times.
There used to be a time when
people would look forward
to seeing the postie.
Any odd jobs you need
me to do while I'm here?
No?
Okay, I'll see you tomorrow morning.
Lovely.
Now it's all parcels
thrown into your bushes.
I'm bringing back the personal touch
in the bright red van.
Royal Male.
- [Chris] But it was time to
decide who'd really solved
the great secondhand delivery van dilemma.
Pulling up to the state-of-the-art
"Top Gear" rapid parcel delivery
assault course test facility
centre.
(suspenseful music)
(Paddy clears throat)
(Freddie chuckling)
You will now tackle a
challenging handling circuit,
delivering packages as you go.
Fastest to complete the round wins.
P.S. Beware of the dog.
- I didn't even listen to the challenge.
I was just looking at that cat.
(suspenseful music)
- [Chris] For Flintoff and
everyone else's benefit, then,
this thorough test of
our delivery vehicles
would now see us take
turns driving a course
specifically designed to
include all the challenges
a busy driver might encounter on a shift.
(dog barking)
- You all right, Jess?
(imitates cat meowing) Shut up.
(Freddie laughing)
Let's deliver.
- And as Postman Pad would now
demonstrate by going first...
Three, two, one, go.
- Oh, oh, hurry.
- [Chris] Those challenges are varied.
- Whoa, hey, hey, hey. (chuckles)
- [Chris] With a handy
sat nav directing us
to the full range of
typical delivery locations.
- [Sat Nav] In 50 metres, turn left.
- [Chris] The course begins
on tight urban streets.
- Ooh, my god.
Geez, these deliveries are everywhere.
- And, of course, for
a delivery to count...
This is quite nice.
- He's going to do it properly, isn't he?
- [Chris] It must be left
in the designated area.
- Thank you.
- [Sat Nav] (beeps) Delivery successful.
- I like that.
- No, I do.
- No, no, I like that.
Next, the course throws up
the dreaded first-floor test.
- Flip the hat, though.
- [Chris] A sweaty dash upstairs
to really get the blood pumping.
- [Sat Nav] (beeps) Delivery successful.
(engine roaring)
- Woohoo!
You all right there, then, Jess?
- [Freddie] He's keen, Pat, isn't he?
- [Chris] As well he should be.
Because it's time for the multi drop zone.
Three addresses, just a few doors apart.
- [Sat Nav] Drop three.
- [Chris] Each one just
begging the question,
do you drive between them?
- [Sat Nav] (beeps) Delivery successful.
- [Chris] Or attack them all on foot?
- [Sat Nav] Drop four.
- Oh, he's dropping them off-
Oh, there he is.
- Yes, he's gonna be tired after this.
- [Paddy] One more stop.
(brakes screeching)
- This is like a really weird
version of "Challenge Anneka."
- [Paddy] Last one.
Get on that.
- Delivery successful.
- This is rigorous.
I think he's got them all so far.
With just two drops remaining,
the course heads out of town,
aiming to test our van's
rural capabilities.
- Drop six.
- Not good.
- Static caravan.
- Ouch, wrong way.
(banana squeaks)
What the (beep)?
- Whoa, whoa.
- Oh, that could have done it.
That could have done it.
- A freaking banana.
- [Chris] Pulling up at the caravan,
no run would be complete
without the always awkward big screen TV.
- [Paddy] One plasma coming up.
- That's in the box.
That's neat and tidy.
And with this textbook run
now drawing to a close,
all that remains is the final drop.
- Come on.
- [Chris] Complete with
every delivery driver's
worst nightmare.
- [Sat Nav] Drop seven.
Warning: Untethered
animal loose on premises.
(Paddy grunts)
- [Paddy] Where's that bloody dog?
Bloody hell, the weight of it.
- Here he goes, here he goes.
- Oh, you got it, Pat.
- Hat's on, hat's on.
- [Freddie] Oh, he's having a go. (laughs)
- [Chris] He's got Jess the cat with him.
- Nice pace, Chris.
He's moving quite well, though.
- [Chris] Now, it's worth mentioning
that any misdeliveries earn
a 20-second time penalty.
(beep)
(Chris and Freddie laughing)
But that was of no concern to Postman Pat.
(dog barking)
- God, there's the dog.
Save yourself, Jess!
(dog barks)
(Paddy gasps)
(dog snarling)
(Paddy grunting)
- Oh, he's got him.
- He's taken down.
(Chris and Freddie laughing)
- [Chris] With a clean sweep of drops,
McGuinness had posted
a very respectable time
of five minutes, 51 seconds.
- [Paddy] Royal Male, son.
We always deliver.
(upbeat music)
- [Chris] A time that
I would now aim to beat
in the Transit.
- Okay, Purple Member,
three, two, one, go.
(brakes screeching)
- Whoa.
- [Paddy] Hope there's
no glassware in there.
- [Sat Nav] Drop number one.
- [Paddy] Rear-wheel drive,
that's where he's got
the advantage, you see.
- [Freddie] But where he
didn't have the advantage...
- [Chris] In you go.
- [Sat Nav] Delivery successful.
- [Freddie] Was when the going got tight.
- Oh, that's two.
Three?
- The Transit is a bit bigger than theirs.
There we go.
- Ooh, is it the house?
- That's four.
- It's the other way.
Feel your way into it, Chris.
- Why is it-
(Paddy and Freddie laughing)
(brakes screeching)
- Six-point turn.
(suspenseful music)
- [Freddie] And as for
the first floor test...
- [Chris] Two.
- [Freddie] That wasn't
much to look at either.
(package crashes)
- Oh!
- He's not got it on.
- He's now throwing it, yeah.
- Oh, he's gone.
He's attempted it, though,
and I reckon you can place, huh.
- [Freddie] You reckon?
- I reckon you can just
give it one of them.
(package crashes)
- Oh.
- [Sat Nav] Delivery successful.
- How's he gonna get it?
He's gonna reverse it.
(brakes screeching)
- The Transit's good at going over curbs.
- Oh.
- No, you can't do that.
That'd be a letter to the company, that.
(engine roaring)
Where the old Purple Sector Delivery
really dropped the ball, though,
was in the multi drop zone.
- Oh, he's missed.
It's in the next guy's drive.
- [Sat Nav] (beeps) Delivery unsuccessful.
20-second penalty.
- [Freddie] Oh, he's trying to lob it in.
- Bollocks.
- Delivery unsuccessful.
- Hell of a mess.
- He's having an absolute nightmare.
- [Sat Nav] Drop five.
(beeps) Delivery unsuccessful.
- Oh, he's missed another.
(rock music)
With the clock ticking away,
Harris bounced out into the countryside,
hoping to redeem himself with
the flat-screen telly drop.
- Now you don't want this
dropping on the floor
by your delivery driver.
This is your plasma.
You've saved up for this.
4K, the lot.
(TV crashes)
Oh my God.
Look at that.
- Oh, no.
- [Sat Nav] (beeps) Delivery successful.
- I'm blowing now.
(Chris sighs)
- [Freddie] To round off
this delivery disaster,
it was just a case of waiting
for our canine friend...
- Where's the dog?
- [Freddie] To put him...
- [Freddie] Out of his misery.
- Where's the dog?
Where's the dog?
- Look how he's running.
- [Freddie] He's got his
shoelaces tied together.
- He's actually running
like he's pooed himself.
- [Freddie] Don't think
about the dog, Chris.
- [Sat Nav] (beeps) Delivery successful.
- Ooh, ooh.
Oh, he's terrified.
(dog barking)
Oh my god, we got it, Chris.
Come on, Harris.
- Finish it.
- He's gonna pull you down.
- Oh no, he got his-
- Ouch.
(dog snarling)
(Chris whimpering)
- Oh.
- Jesus.
- Do you want a bone?
Would you like a Bonio?
Bonio?
- What we've got here from Chris Harris
is a second-class delivery.
(dog snarling)
- [Chris] How about a steak?
Okay, with three missed deliveries
resulting in a seven
minute, 26 second run,
it'd be fair to say I hadn't
gone purple in every sector.
(upbeat music)
So with Paddy in his Caddy
still the team to beat,
could FredEx in his sporty
Astra deliver the goods?
(suspenseful music)
- Now, remember, that is a plasma.
- The way it's
ratchet-strapped to the roof,
it's now three plasmas.
- Are you ready?
- Yeah.
- FredEx.
(vehicle roaring)
Three, two, one, deliver.
- Go, Fred.
- FredEx, hey.
Oh, oh.
(brakes screeching)
- Ooh, no, this is done.
- Here we go.
- This is it.
- Is he gonna give it some?
- Ooh, it's tight.
Wait a minute, look at the street.
Some dodgy parking 'round here.
(brakes screech)
- [Paddy] Ooh, he hit the house.
- He's just driven straight into a house.
- Where's my parcel?
Where's the numbers?
One.
(package crashing)
- Should he leave his
name and number there?
- [Paddy] A nervy start
from the boy racer,
but let's be honest, the next drop...
- [Freddie] Oh, I'm not going up there.
- Was right up his street.
Oh, he's on the roof.
(package crashing)
- Delivery successful.
- Hey.
- He's got it in a box still, though.
What a swine.
(suspenseful music)
- [Paddy] Oh, yes,
at FredEx, speed is everything.
(engine roaring)
- Whoa, slow down.
There's something in the
back wouldn't like that.
- [Paddy] And with two
drops done already...
- Six.
- Next up was the multi drop masterclass.
Now he's got the arm.
- Ooh.
- Look.
Oh, he's got that in as well.
- [Freddie] Delivery.
- That's in as well.
- Delivery successful.
- Delivery.
That'll do.
- [Sat Nav] (beep) Delivery unsuccessful.
- He hasn't got that
one in as well, has he?
- [Paddy] He hadn't.
But sprinting out of town...
- Ooh.
- Like a rough ride.
- I gotta get the ratchet off.
- [Paddy] Flintoff was soon
dispatching the big screen TV
with the now customary FredEx touch.
(TV crashes)
- Oh my god.
- Delivery successful.
- It's in the box.
(Paddy chuckling)
- What was that?
- [Paddy] And pulling up to the final drop
with a couple of penalties against him...
- Loving those ratchet straps.
- [Paddy] Stealing the
delivery driver top spot
would need every ounce of
that trademark FredEx pace.
- [Sat Nav] Delivery successful.
(suspenseful music)
- Here we go.
- Look at his face.
(dog barking)
- I've got this.
I've got it.
(dog snarling)
Oh no.
Oh, you win, you win.
(Chris laughing)
Look, you win.
Good boy.
(audience applauding)
- I'm not happy about this.
No, I'm not happy about this.
- It's okay.
- No, I'm not.
- You wouldn't do it again.
- You gotta know.
(Freddie laughing)
You gotta know.
So I know the question on everyone's lips-
- Have we totally lost our minds?
- Not that, no.
(audience laughing)
Who takes the delivery
driver bragging rights?
Did FredEx manage to beat Postman Pad?
Well, I've got the results here, folks.
(audience applauding)
- No. (chuckles)
- No, we can forget Purple Sector.
You are a nightmare.
You out of the running.
We know that.
(audience laughing)
It's down to me and you, Fred.
Right, I've got the times here.
I managed five minutes, 51
seconds with no missed drops.
- Ooh.
(audience applauding)
Fred, you managed four
minutes, 47 seconds,
but two missed drops.
- Ooh.
- What does that mean?
what does that mean?
- Resulting in a time
of also five minutes,
27 seconds.
FredEx delivers.
(audience applauding)
- Thank you.
Thank you, Pad.
Thank you, Postman.
Thank you.
- I'm sorry, stop it.
- It's fine, it's fine.
- This is absolutely outrageous.
Half your packages were destroyed.
- Exactly, only half.
Big delivery companies
could learn a thing or two
from my care and attention.
- So what have we learned here?
- If you want a cheap van to
deliver very small packages,
and you're not too fussed if
they get there in one piece,
get yourself an Astra.
- And the most important lesson.
Taxidermy cats, utterly terrifying.
Stuff of nightmares.
- Yes, horrendous.
- Whoa.
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
- Don't you ever, ever
speak about Jess like that.
- Oh. (laughs)
(audience laughing)
Right, that is not right.
That is not right.
- She has got feelings.
(Freddie laughs)
Go on, Jess, run free.
(Paddy and Freddie laughing)
(audience applauding)
Anyhow, we've got to move on to something
a little less weird,
because to end this series,
we're taking on our
biggest challenge today.
We're gonna give you some advice
that's actually useful in the real world.
- Easy, Pad, don't scare the horses.
- Chris, take it away.
- Family cars.
There's hundreds out there to choose from.
But if you're in the market for a new one,
how do you even start to make a choice?
- Well, fear you not because
"Top Gear" is here to help.
(wind rustling)
(birds chirping)
(airy orchestral music)
Nowadays, when it comes to family cars,
the range of options out
there is frankly baffling.
From your practical,
battery-powered spaceships,
like the Kia EV6.
- Here we go.
- [Paddy] To seven-seat
Dacia people-carriers
that cost less than
your average supermini.
All this room for 16 grand.
I mean, crikey, there
are even estate cars,
like this Alpina B3,
solely designed for families
that prefer to arrive sideways.
(brakes screeching)
There she goes. (laughs)
It just brings out your inner child.
The point is,
there are now more to choose
from than ever before.
So with the producers helping to gather
a 50-strong assortment
of the newest, most interesting,
and best-selling examples on the market.
- [Freddie] That's a lot of family cars.
- [Paddy] Our job is to find you
the best of the lot.
- [Chris] Suits you, sir.
- Oh, look at this.
Family cars for every
taste, every occasion.
- [Chris] That's what it says.
A bit of a mixed bag, isn't there?
- It is a mixed bag.
- I'm gonna go for a rootle.
- A rootle?
- Ooh, I like that.
- Right, where we going here?
Where are we going?
- I've seen where I'm going straight away.
I've had a couple of these over the years.
They're not the cheapest of things.
But I tell you what,
Loads of space, loads of room in the back.
You can throw all the kids in.
They can kick the seats.
They can do what they want.
It's fine.
It's a Disco.
- Look at this little Peugeot thing here.
Look at that.
That's a great-looking car.
508 with three yellow lines,
which must denote some sportiness.
- [Freddie] This is
bordering on midlife crisis.
- It is.
- But you get your family in.
I like it. (laughs)
- So do I.
- How much is it?
- It's 56 grand.
- Stop it.
- 56 grand for a Peugeot.
- All right, let's have a look.
What else have we got here?
Here we go.
- Can we just stop and say how
good Kias look at the moment?
- I've always been a fan of the Kia.
- [Chris] But these were
a joke 15 years ago.
Now they look better than
all the German stuff.
- Now I'm just speaking for the dads now.
Every dad wants to rock up at school,
knowing they can absolutely
blast the back doors off anything.
That sounds wrong, but
you know what I mean.
And this is what we've
got with the old M5 Comp.
But when you get inside
it, not very practical.
Cup holders are quite small.
Side bin's tiny.
- [Chris] Oldest family
car maker, Vauxhall.
- What's the family, the Borrowers?
(Chris laughs)
Where do you put your family in that?
- Here we go.
I mean, just look at the storage in here.
Look at that.
- Come on, this is all you need.
It's massive, it's comfortable.
- It is.
And I know it's a Volvo,
but it does nothing for me.
(Paddy sighs)
- That's what you want.
- We gotta do something about this.
There's too many cars here.
- Where'd you go with it?
- I don't know.
Pad?
- There's something very reassuring
about the knobs on a Volvo.
- Don't do that.
- Just lovely action on them.
- Don't do that. (chuckles)
- Everything's good in the world.
You get in a Volvo,
you get out and you go,
"Actually, we're all right."
- Right, we got too many cars here.
We need to find a way of removing some.
We need to get some perspective, okay?
- [Paddy] Huh?
- [Chris] We need to get some
height on it, over there.
- Height?
- Straight to the point.
- Chris Harris, what do you know?
(crane whirring)
Chris, what are we doing up here?
- We're about to do some whittling.
Not woodwork, either.
Right, so the starting
point here surely has to be
anything over 40 grand's gotta go
because that's not an
affordable family car
that can be used most of the time, is it?
- 40 grand?
- But for the price of cars,
that's gonna be a lot of cars.
- Yeah.
- Also, 40 grand is when the posh car tax,
the premium car tax comes in.
- Cost of living crisis,
gotta think practical.
Stand back.
- Yeah.
- Right, get rid of the 40 grand-plus's.
Are you okay?
- Whoa! (beep)
(Freddie and Paddy laughing)
(upbeat music)
- Oh, the Taycan's gone.
- Oh, wow, Exodus.
- Giulia's gone, one Rover.
- Oh.
- There's the M5, Chris.
- Wave a goodbye kiss.
- Oh no.
- It's like a giant game
of "Guess Who?" isn't it?
- It is.
It is like "Guess Who?"
- Just drive off.
- In an important copyright sense,
it's quite unlike "Guess Who?"
you know what I mean?
- Yeah, yeah, of course.
Yeah, it is, yeah.
- Certainly.
Right, okay.
- Now, I gotta be honest,
I do love a whittle.
- You do?
- (laughs) You're a whittler.
- I love a whittle.
(Freddie laughs)
Can I have a go at it?
- Yes.
- I'm getting into it now.
- All right.
I love this.
Honda Jazz, that's gone.
- [Freddie] What?
- What criteria are you using
to get rid of the Honda Jazz?
- I just hate it.
- You can't get rid of
cars 'cause you hate them.
It's not how it works.
- Hatering's not a category, hatering?
- No, no it's not.
- Well, I'll tell you what, then.
Real-world running costs.
- Yes.
- It's all about the MPG.
- Yep.
- You're a family.
Petrol prices, diesel prices,
they're through the roof.
Gotta keep them down.
So I'm looking minimum
50 miles per gallon.
- What about electric?
- Yeah, that's a good point.
- By definition,
it has to be more efficient.
- Exactly, electric can stay.
- So anything over 50 MPG
and electric can stay.
- Electric's staying?
- Okay.
- Electric's staying, yeah.
- Okay, got you.
- Right, okay.
- Got them?
- Anything under 50 miles
to the gallon can go.
(upbeat music)
- Oh, oh, oh.
- Whoa.
- The Dacia Jogger's gone.
- The Jogger's gone?
- Goodbye, the Jogger.
- Why's the jogger gone?
- 50 MPG.
- Disco's gone.
Disco's a great family car.
- Ooh, ooh.
- Another Honda gone.
- Aw.
- That's a surprise.
- [Paddy] So the Jazz has stayed,
but that Honda, the CR-V's gone.
- [Freddie] You can't get rid
of that Jazz, Pad. (laughs)
- Wrong Honda.
- Oh.
- I want that Berlingo gone,
but I think it's staying.
- Yeah.
- The Berlingo's gonna be
here for the whole day.
- You reckon?
- Yeah.
That is some very strong culling.
But now over to Fred.
What is your whittle?
- Now I need space, not just for myself.
Kids' cricket bags, I need boot space.
I'm gonna say anything under
500-liters boot space is off.
- [Chris] But that is a harsh cull.
- Anything under 500-liters boot space,
hit the road, Jack.
Come on, Jazz.
- Yes! (laughs)
- It's gone.
- Get out of here.
- Oh.
Where are they all going?
- Wow.
- Ooh, dear me.
- [Paddy] You have decimated
the field there, Andrew. (whistles)
- When I whittle, Chris, it this whittle.
- Complete carnage.
- And, well,
science has spoken gentlemen.
We are not left with much.
(jazzy music)
- [Freddie] What we are left with, though,
are nine very tidy options.
From the ever-popular Nissan Qashqai,
to the clue's-in-the-title Skoda Superb,
or even the much-harder-to-love
Citroen Berlingo.
These are all cars with a
generous amount of boot space
that start at less than 40 grand,
and a spec that'll do north
of 50 miles to the gallon.
But we're not done yet.
(suspenseful music)
Because to whittle it down some more,
I'd come up with a drag
race with a difference.
- [Chris] Fred, why are you so
much further forward than me?
- Because this, Christopher,
is a price handicap.
The cheapest car at the front.
The more expensive the car,
the further back you start.
- Did you choose the car you're in?
- [Freddie] No, this car chose me.
(Chris laughing)
- [Paddy] Yes, in a surprise to us all,
Flintoff had come up
with a rather elegant way
of testing which of
our nine remaining cars
represent the best balance
of price and performance.
A half-mile drag race
where the most expensive
contender is tested,
the Skoda Enyaq iV
would start at the back.
The rest of the field then
receiving a 10-meter headstart
for every thousand
pounds cheaper they cost.
Last three to cross the
line are eliminated.
(suspenseful music)
(engine roaring)
Three, two, one, go.
Whoa.
There we go.
The Arkana's off.
- Go on, the Hyundai.
Bye-bye, Superb.
- I'll be screaming past them.
- Go, go, nothing at me.
- Done the Skoda.
- So I'm going backwards here.
This is just a day out.
Paddy's gone.
- There's Flintoff. (laughs)
Wowzers, this thing flies.
- Oh, the Berlingo, that is embarrassing.
I've been passed by a Berlingo and Harris
on the outside in the Skoda.
- We've got the Renault.
- Come on, we're over the line.
Doom the Qashi.
(cars zooming)
Go on.
- [Chris] Third, we'll take third.
- [Freddie] Not last.
I started at the front, I'm last.
- A nice victory there for the Tucson.
- This thing's got some
heart, I'm telling you.
- I've gotta say, the
Arkana just doesn't go.
By the time I get the
lads to cricket in this,
we'd have Blair turnovers.
(Chris laughing)
(upbeat music)
So the bang-for-your-buck drag race
had eliminated the electric Skoda Enyaq,
the Volkswagen Tiguan Allspace,
and the Renault Arkana.
Now we needed to get six down to three.
And with the pack so tightly matched,
the only way to do that was by unleashing
the motoring journalist
- Hi, lads.
- Oh, god, he's got clipboards.
- [Freddie] He's got three of them.
- Let's get down to the
nitty-gritty of car testing.
This is the real stuff.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Clipboard each.
- Thank you.
- Always leave the pen under there
with the nib at the bottom.
- Oh god.
- Better access.
- Okay.
- Right, here we go.
Legroom.
- Ooh.
- Oh. I'd say the-
- I need legroom.
- Exactly, we've got the
perfect dummy for this.
- Yes.
- Okay?
- So I'm a dummy?
- I'd say standard
legroom test should be a Flintoff
sitting behind a Flintoff.
Would you agree?
- I like that.
I like that.
- Okay.
Okay, the Skoda Superb
is known to be a leader
in this field.
- Ooh.
- I don't like the way
you're holding that.
That is too low.
I want it here and I want it here.
- That's where I go.
- Right.
Now, out you come, Mr. Flintoff, please.
In the back now.
Okay, not every family comes from
the Flintoff end of the gene pool.
- Kids 6'4", 6'3".
- [Chris] But we all know legroom is key
to a happy backseat.
- [Paddy] Are you comfortable?
- [Freddie] Tell you what,
that's not bad, that.
That's all right, that.
- That is dead impressive, Andrew.
- Do you know what?
Even head room's fine.
- That is four.
- I'll give them that.
- Four points.
And you'd be surprised how
often the posher badges
trade this crucial detail
for sleeker styling.
- I'm just...
I can't...
No, I can't get in it.
- Come on, get in.
- No, I can't, look.
- In we go, right.
- Yeah.
- How far could you travel like that?
- [Freddie] I don't wanna
travel anywhere like this.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- There's headroom, no legroom.
- That's not really working, is it?
- Not a chance.
- [Freddie] Not a chance.
Next on Harris's clipboard of truth
was that great leveller,
Isofix child seats.
- Let's choose this little
Skoda here, the Octavia.
- [Freddie] I'm on my
fourth kid with these.
- It's great, you're in.
- I'm in?
- You know, that's the
easiest one I've ever put in.
- Is it?
- Oh, let's get a five
on that.
- Seriously, bar none.
- Get a five on that.
Now do you want us to pop one
of them in the driving seat
for future challenges?
- There's no need for that at all.
Right, next car.
- [Freddie] With the Octavia
taking the Isofix top spot,
second place went to the
mercurial Audi Q3 Sportback.
- I'm straight in there.
I'm already at the McDonald's drive-thru
buying a kid's meal right now.
My children are so happy.
- [Freddie] And rounding
out the top three,
our drag race winner, the Hyundai Tucson.
- Here it is.
- Go on, then.
- [Paddy] There she goes.
- [Freddie] Closing in
on the big decision,
Harris had one more trick up his clipboard
to get us over the line.
- This is arguably the most
important test of the lot,
starting with the Qashqai.
Okay, you're in a car park.
You try and get your mobile
phone out of your pocket
and you drop it between the seat
and centre console.
- Oh, no, you don't.
- You now have to show us
how easy or difficult it is
to retrieve that phone.
This is critical to all car purchases.
Ready?
Three, two, one, and go, Andrew.
Show us what you can do.
- Retrieved.
- That's incredible.
For a hand that size in a car like this,
I think that's superb.
- Oh, look at this.
- Are you ready, Chris?
- [Chris] Yep, let's go.
- [Freddie] This isn't too easy.
- [Paddy] I've gotta say
the Berlingo's a five.
- It's a five.
- On the strength of that,
would you buy a Berlingo?
- Yes.
Here we go.
Ready?
- Are you ready?
- Yeah.
- Uh-oh.
- Oh.
You've done me there.
- I'm known to be fingers.
- Oh my god.
- It's gone now.
- No.
- Oh, it's a nightmare.
It's a nightmare.
- That's a one.
- Oh, no.
- Zero.
- Zero, mark it down.
- No, no, no, no.
- Paddy, you can keep the form.
- Geez, I can't even get my hand back.
Is that in there?
- Chaps?
- Yeah.
- Science is over.
- Mm.
- Okay, we've now gotta whittle
down to the final three.
Are we in agreement
that the Hyundai is in the
top three for all of us?
- Yes.
- So that goes through.
- Done.
- The Skoda Octavia is in my top three.
Is it in yours?
- Yes.
- [Chris] Is it in yours?
- Ooh, this is fantastic.
This is what happens-
- It's good.
- I think we're gonna struggle now.
We've got a Skoda in already,
so we don't need two.
- [Paddy] Can I throw a curve ball in?
- Yeah.
- Go on.
- Berlingo.
- Why?
- Get in the-
- Hear me out, hear me out.
- Okay, go on.
- It's the only car
we've got that's full EV.
- Yeah.
- That's important.
That's important.
- The phone test, five out of five.
These are the ones where when
you're in a car with the kids,
them are the problems you have.
- That is a strong argument.
- Loads of boot space.
- I'll give you the
practicality.
- Yep.
- All over it.
Also, we've not mentioned this.
- Sliding door.
- Wonderful, practical.
- I know.
Okay, I'm gonna go with McGuinness.
The Berlingo stays in.
It's the quirky choice.
- Right.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- So we've got them.
We've got our three.
- Science, science.
(upbeat music)
- [Chris] Now that, ladies and gentlemen,
is how you use a clipboard.
Because whether it's
the perfectly practical
diesel Skoda Octavia estate,
the really rather handsome
hybrid Hyundai Tucson,
or the staggeringly
spacious Citroen e-Berlingo,
pick one of these for your next family car
and you won't be disappointed.
But we tasked ourselves
with picking a winner.
And to do that,
McGuinness reckoned he'd
come up with the ideal test.
- So the last one, real-world experience.
Life on the road with
your family in the car.
That's the next test.
- What's that test?
- Glad you asked.
It's a classic seat-switch race.
We're gonna set up from here.
You've got a stopwatch, start that.
I'm gonna go around to
the little box over there,
I'm gonna stop in the box,
then we're gonna swap round,
in the car, anti-clockwise.
Me, you, you here.
Then you set off driving
all the way back around
over the finish line,
stop the watch.
- How often does the child
come from the back and drive the car?
- Well, every time when Pad's driving.
- Correct.
It's the easiest way.
You can have a beer then, can't you?
(Freddie laughing)
Right, come on, kids.
Great.
- Ready?
- Three, two, one, go.
- Let's go.
(upbeat music)
- [Paddy] Let's face it,
the very best family journeys
are the ones that are over and done with
as fast as possible.
- Could go to this thing,
doesn't it?
- Oh, wow, yes.
That's all right, that.
- [Paddy] And to keep
the peace along the way,
you really need as much room
for everyone as you can get.
- Paddy.
- Switch it.
- Swap, go.
- I don't like this at all.
- You come back here.
You come back here.
(Chris laughing)
You're too big and you tickle people.
- Don't do that.
- Let's do that.
- Grab my foot. (laughs)
Grab my foot.
- Ow. (laughs)
Ow.
- Okay, come on. (laughs)
What if you've got my foot?
- Ah.
- Actually got my other one.
- Hang on, the seatbelt.
- Oh.
- Whoa, that's quick.
- [Chris] There she goes.
- [Paddy] And that's why
when it comes to finding
the ultimate family car...
She's lively.
She really is the quickest of the lot.
You want to be looking
out for that magic place
where space meets pace.
- You better get in that.
- Oh no.
- Oh my god, here we go.
- Oh, stop.
- I'm a child, I'm a child.
- Oh. (laughing)
- Stop it, stop it.
- I like you down there.
- [Chris] Here we go.
Quick.
Stop.
(stopwatch beeps)
What's the time?
- 1:34:16.
- Ooh.
- Tell you what, I am mighty
impressed by this thing.
At just over a minute 1/2 to get round,
the hybrid Tucson had laid
down a serious benchmark.
The only question now was,
could it be beaten by the e-Berlingo?
- Three, two, one.
(stopwatch beeps)
- Ooh.
- Oh, it's flat on then.
- What's going, Fred?
- Flat on.
- Let it go.
Or the Octavia.
- Go.
(stopwatch beeps)
- Stalled at the line.
- Oh, you think so?
(rock music)
- [Freddie] Oh, it's a roller, isn't it?
Oh.
- It's anything but a roller.
- Oh, oh.
- Oh.
- Use all the track,
get her out there.
- All right,
well, we're gonna get
a little nibble there.
- Get her out there.
Get her out there.
(suspenseful music)
- Right, now can you stop in the box.
- I like it.
- Ah.
- We can walk around this car.
- I'm not sure about this.
We're about to get into it.
- Whoa.
- Ooh.
- Oh, I missed it.
- Oh, you missed the box,
you idiot.
- You missed it.
(elegant orchestral music)
- I'm gonna gonna come back to you.
I'm gonna come back to you.
- That's not a problem.
- Come on, get in there.
- Look at that.
- I'll just move over.
- There we go, Pad.
- That is just quality.
- There we go.
- That is lovely stuff.
- May we, may we.
- That is.
That's a demonstration of
the Berlingo's real talent.
- Move over.
- You go first, you go first.
- I'll move over.
(Paddy laughing)
- Get off.
- Come on, son.
(Freddie and Paddy laughing)
(upbeat music)
No, no. (laughs)
- Ah, no. (laughs)
- Oh, my undies have gone.
Oh, my undies have gone. (laughs)
(car horn blaring)
No, look.
Look at my undies.
(Paddy laughing)
You don't do that to your kids.
We're off.
(upbeat music)
- [Paddy] After a very
revealing seat swap...
- I'm not even bothered now.
I've got my pants around my ankles.
Look where my pants are.
- [Paddy] It was now just
a short sprint to the line.
- Come on.
- Berlingo, go, go.
- [Paddy] To discover
which of our finalists
would take family car glory.
(stopwatch beeps)
(Chris sighs)
(Paddy groans)
- He has flesh on that seat.
(orchestral music)
And with a time of one minute 41,
and just over two minutes respectively,
neither the palatial but
ponderous e-Berlingo,
nor the speedy but snug Octavia estate
had quite done enough
to knock the perfectly-pitched
Tucson hybrid
off the top spot.
Which meant, after what
can only be described
as a pretty rigorous day's testing...
- Look at his.
(Paddy laughing)
Look. (laughs)
- No, it's not funny.
- Oh.
- [Paddy] In the end, there
could be only one conclusion.
- That Hyundai is the best car.
- Yeah, that's what science says.
- You wouldn't have anything else.
- Yep, exactly.
- For that money,
with those criteria.
- Yeah.
Is that how you did it on Auto Car?
- Not quite, no.
(grand orchestral music)
(audience applauding)
- That was a very good car.
- Very, very good.
- Love it, love it.
- No complaints.
No complaints.
- I'll admit, a wrestling
match in the back of a Hyundai,
it's not the most conventional way
to decide between a bunch of family cars.
(audience laughing)
But I think we all agree on this one.
We actually came up with the right answer.
The car we'd recommend
is the Hyundai Tucson.
(audience applauding)
- So I tell you what,
we may be mavericks, but we get results.
- Correct.
It's a very good car.
And it's further evidence
that Hyundai is smashing it at the moment,
making proper hot hatches,
interesting electric cars,
worthy family cars.
They're on a roll.
- Well, what a way to sign off.
Because that's the end of
the show, and the series.
- [Audience] Aw.
- But we'll see you all next year.
- [Audience] Yay.
- Thanks a bunch for watching.
Goodnight.
(audience applauding)
(upbeat rock music)
(upbeat rock music continues)
(no audio)