CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Hello. Welcome to Top Gear,
where tonight we're mixing it up.
We're going to do the show
a little bit differently.
It's in 3D. Raargh!
No, I'm only joking.
Fred, take it away.
Because we're not kicking off
with him skidding around
in a shiny supercar.
Or trying to kill Fred
in new and inventive ways.
No, we're kicking off with
a question - what if?
What if we could actually make a
genuine difference to a few lives,
give a bit back?
So we're kicking off with
a little experiment.
In the world of motorsports, life
at the top is fast, glamorous
and very exclusive.
No matter how talented you might be,
the simple truth is that,
without the right connections
and a whole heap of cash,
it's nigh on impossible to crack.
So here's the experiment.
What would happen if we developed
our very own race team,
a race team of young drivers and
mechanics,
who haven't got the connections
and who haven't got the cash,
and dropped them right in at the
deep end?
That deep end looks like this -
contesting a round of the
prestigious GT Cup race series...
..at Donington Park.
800 hopefuls applied
and, from them, we selected 13
of the brightest young talents
in the UK...
..and set up a test day to see
what they were made of.
Today means a lot to me because it's
given me an opportunity
that I didn't think I'd ever have.
I'm meeting a lot of people,
learning a lot from other people.
I started racing when I was an
11-year-old.
I've been driving since I was three.
I'm here for a bit of mechanics
today, working on the MX-5 here,
do a bit of bolt and grease.
The Top Gear race team needs
two mechanics and two drivers.
So, to help choose them and then
train them up,
I called in professional
race team Paddock Motorsport.
Well, today we're looking for a
diamond in the rough, basically.
We're not looking
for a finished article.
We just want somebody who's
good at taking instruction
and is very mouldable.
These guys are going to come
in with experience from other
disciplines, so it's very important
that we can understand
how to take that forward.
Louis, take your time with the
gears, buddy. Don't rush it.
All right, mate. If you want to
crack into it. The tools are here.
A good mechanic needs a very good
attention to detail,
basically for fault-finding,
anything that's happened on the
circuit.
I love being a mechanic
because you spend so much time
and energy working on this one thing
to get that little bit faster.
The youngsters are a talented bunch,
one that knows all too well
that skill alone isn't enough
to get to the top.
I haven't got loads of money
just to chuck at a car.
I'd say money plays a big part in
it, yeah,
Money and opportunity, definitely.
With so much to play for,
Paddock Motorsport can only choose
those that show the most potential.
And, once the dust settles,
we have our four.
In the garage, mechanics Lillie
and Callum.
Out on track,
drivers Louis and Ollie.
With the race team assembled,
now it was time to train them.
Boot camp starts just a few days
later,
at Pembrey racetrack in
Carmarthenshire...
..where Louis is straight out on
track with driving coach Michael.
Open that up wider.
Good lad.
Not messing around, is he?
No, going for it.
Back in his hometown of Croydon,
our first young driver's racing
career has so far played out
at the local rental karting centre.
At the moment, I'm working at
Gatwick Airport as a ramp agent,
where we handle people's suitcases.
It's usually me saving up my weekly
pay
and just putting it aside for
go-karting.
Louis has the raw potential,
but this experiment
will be a big test.
When I got the phone call
saying I'm in the team,
I was just so over the moon.
Just got to make the most of it.
Mate, really good. Really good.
Good lad.
Feeling all right? Yeah, good.
Totally different to karting.
It might be new territory for Louis,
but the Paddock race engineers
reveal he's already had
a promising start.
Yeah. On your last lap there, Louis,
you were... You got yourself to
within five seconds of Martin.
Wow.
Can you just slow it down
a little bit, like, this...?!
It's a good start, guys.
In the garage, meanwhile, mechanics
Lillie and Callum
are already well
into their engineering crash course
on Paddock's second race-spec MX-5.
These coils commonly fail
due to the heat.
That's why after every session
we take them out.
Two kids coming in as apprentices
will not even get within touching
distance of a car on a team for the
first three or even four years.
So the guys out there driving,
you can actually be in a car
driving one quicker
than you can be a mechanic
out here in the pit lane.
Absolutely. I mean, the biggest
thing to remember
is the responsibility.
One mistake, one missed
bolt - it's someone's life.
That's totally shocked me,
the three or four-year thing.
I never realised that, myself.
Our young mechanics are definitely
in at the deep end
but Cornwall-based Lillie
and Lincolnshire lad Callum
have both grown up with that
mechanical mind-set
that might just help them swim.
Excellent stuff.
I like living in my lorry
because it's quiet.
No-one's around and I can do
whatever I want, really,
be in the shed on the cars
till whatever time.
Recently bought a couple
of bangers, got to strip them
and then build them
ready for racing.
First of all, before she'd done
the mechanics,
she used to do show jumping.
She came back from a show and said,
"I don't want to do this any more.
"I want to do bangers."
Started at 11 doing banger racing.
Pretty much smash everyone else
up and hope you don't hurt yourself,
really!
Every time we'd blow up an engine,
me and my brother would change
engines together.
I love being a mechanic because
you find a problem, you fix it,
you get dirty and it's satisfying.
At 16, I started here as a HGV
mechanic apprentice.
Morning, Kev. Morning!
I worked in the garage
with my dad and his friend.
It was brilliant.
It's a good atmosphere.
After school, I went to college
and got an apprenticeship.
I did two years in a
Land Rover garage.
It seems to come easy.
If you kind of think about it
logically, it all clicks together.
Just something I really enjoy.
Back out on track,
driver Ollie's training with Michael
is now also well under way.
Close the car in. Cross those arms.
And back home, in North Yorkshire,
this is a young man who spends every
spare minute in or around race cars.
I've never really been an academic
lad.
I'd much rather spend my evenings
in the garage with my dad,
tinkering with the cars.
Ollie, his dad, mum and brother
all compete on the dirt oval tracks
of National Autograss racing.
And, to help pay his way, Ollie
works full-time building generators.
The money that goes into the car
comes in your pocket
and goes out the next minute.
What else would you want
to spend your money on at 19?
Not many nights out are allowed, but
yeah, it's good.
There's lots of other sacrifices
as well.
It's like we don't do foreign
holidays.
Our holidays are spent in a camper
van, racing Saturday and Sunday,
back home and back to work
to earn some more pennies
to do it all again next week.
A former junior and open champion,
Ollie has plenty of race experience.
Down to quarter to three
and cross your arms,
if you need a bit more lock.
But the move from dirt to tarmac
is not to be underestimated.
What was he saying about feeding
the wheel?
Was that a habit from
grass-tracking?
Basically, because we only
go around an oval,
I don't cross my arms.
I've never crossed my arms because
that's quite slow in our sport.
The reason he's saying that is,
if you keep your hands there,
you know which way the steering
wheel is pointing. Yeah.
So, if ever you get out of shape,
you know, you just point
and that's kind of where you're
pointing.
To get you out of trouble. Yeah.
It's been an intensive first
day for the team,
but then, with the challenge
that lies ahead of them,
it needed to be.
Seven weeks' time,
they're going to be on track
with professional drivers. Yeah.
When you tell me things
like that and I think about it,
I get very anxious.
Seven weeks, seven weeks!
It's not a lot of time, is it?
It's a tall order.
By doing something like this,
we're giving them a chance to sort
of fulfil their dreams,
but also to show their talents.
For me, personally, it's a real
passion project because it's nice
to be in a position to give
them that chance now
and to watch them grow.
The dream for me in doing the film
like this is someone notices them.
While the mechanics spend the next
week getting stuck in at Paddock HQ,
driver coaching steps up a gear.
Louis and Ollie have been studying
hard to get their race licences.
Your chariot awaits, sir.
And now, out on track,
it's their first ever go
on a live circuit in the MX-5.
My only concern for them today
would be
if the nerves got the better of
them.
Fast cars coming
up and overtaking them...
OK. Stay on your line, buddy.
Stay on your line.
Michael takes each driver out
on track for tuition.
But, in busy traffic, mistakes are
made.
Get the line right, mate,
before we try and carry the speed.
You're trying to carry the
speed too soon.
Let it flow. Let it come to you.
All too soon,
the team will be back at Donington
for the GT Cup.
There's no choice but to dust
off and keep pushing forward.
Training reaches the halfway point
and the team are at
Cadwell Park in Lincolnshire.
The Paddock experts need to see
how they're shaping up
by giving them their first race
together in the Mazda SuperCup.
Cadwell couldn't be a more difficult
place to bring two newbies
for their first ever race weekend
in a car they're unfamiliar with.
It's tight, it's narrow,
it's undulating, it's unsighted.
Mazda weekends, you never know
what can get thrown at you,
so anything can happen.
The team has been practising
at Cadwell for a couple of days.
And the challenging circuit hasn't
just been a test for the drivers.
First practice, he broke his
gearbox,
so came back in and changed that.
He went out again and then went
in the wall
and bent his steering rack,
so we had to change that.
Gearbox weren't too bad. The
steering rack's just fiddly.
Cos the radiator's in the way.
all the belts and everything.
Don't break the car.
We haven't got any more.
Yeah, try not to.
But, as the more relaxed practice
sessions end, the mood shifts.
The focus is now on the team's
first ever competitive race.
It ain't right. Oh, BLEEP this
all. No need, is there?
All right, buddy, you ready? Yeah.
Forget about yesterday. Yeah.
Focus on today, all right? All
right.
You'll be fine. Good luck.
All the best. Thank you.
Louis and Ollie join a 27-car grid,
one that's split into two classes.
Pros starting towards the front
and the amateur club class
that the boys have qualified
in the middle of
makes up the back of the field.
I'm nervous. I just started
getting a little bit of butterflies
in the stomach for them.
Five-second...
Come on.
Lights on.
And we're off. Go!
Go, my boys!
Whoa! Whoo!
The first corner, here we go.
Got to watch this.
They're round. They're OK.
I've driven round here.
It's a tricky circuit.
It is. There's no room for error.
He's done him. He's gone back in
front, yeah.
Good lad, Louis.
First overtake. Come on, man.
Louis is chasing Ollie down now.
He's trying, he's trying!
Louis now has got to be careful
because he's trying to attack Ollie
but he's also going to get
under pressure from the car behind.
Ah, they've muscled him out.
Yeah, and he's lost two spots there.
Oh, no, no.
That's the inexperience,
though, you know.
Ugh!
The boys are training to
be a two-driver team, though.
And up the field, Ollie is going
from strength to strength.
Ollie is running two seconds
a lap quicker than
the cars in front of him, so he's
gaining on that pack. Fantastic.
Go on, Ollie! Go on, Ollie!
Go on, son!
They're out there, they're racing,
they're mixing it up with people
who've been doing this for years.
Yep.
Chequered flag.
Yeah, well done, Ollie!
With neither driver having
raced on a tarmac circuit before,
it's a solid debut.
Ollie crossing the line
sixth in class...
Go on, Louis!
..and Louis coming in eighth.
Well done!
Heart rate was going for a bit.
No, it was good.
Got your first race start under the
belt,
you've been overtaking people,
you've been getting stuck in.
I can tell you're not happy.
But I'm happy that you're not happy,
because if you were happy then
there's something wrong.
If you've got that driver mentality,
you always want more.
You can come in and win the race and
you'll be wanting more. Yeah.
So tomorrow, we go again.
Well done, boys.
Well done, well done, well done.
Literally, I just want to
go out right now and just race,
to get all my frustration out.
There's no time
to dwell on mistakes,
training for the drivers
is constant.
Every time they get
behind the wheel, it's followed up
by a full analysis of the drive with
the Paddock coaching team.
I think where you were getting
a little bit frustrated,
where you had your bit of a moment,
I think there, was just trying
to go just too deep.
Going through the data
has been amazing.
Giving me them tips,
just where I can find
that last few tenth of a second to
improve my overall lap.
I know what to do for my
races tomorrow.
So, hopefully, I have no
problems and it'll be a good race.
With the two races left to run that
weekend, the next morning,
Louis and Ollie set out to put
the theory into practice.
There goes Oliver Hall up
the inside, that was a late move.
Can he hold the inside line?
He's later on the brakes and
he will slip through.
Proving a very spectacular driver
to watch, is Oliver.
The first race gets under way well,
with Ollie maintaining his
impressive form.
Oliver Hall,
very quick reactions there.
As the race progresses, though,
the real star student is Louis.
And Louis Smithen has got himself
ahead of Oliver Hall, look.
Really coming on strong in the
second half of the race.
After a hard-fought
battle to the line...
Oh, big contact!
And that's Oliver Hall involved.
..Ollie hangs on to finish
fourth in class.
And with Louis a place ahead of him,
Team Top Gear has its first podium.
Well done, Louis. Come on, lad.
Get in there! Well done. Thank you.
Good stuff.
It's a huge boost for the team.
And Louis isn't done yet.
The lights go out,
we're away and racing.
In the last battle of the weekend,
a mistake from Ollie sees him
playing catch-up from the off.
But Louis is in the zone.
Turning all that data,
the analysis and the coaching
into a clean race to the finish.
A really impressive end
to his MX-5 SuperCup debut.
The second podium of the weekend,
Louis Smithen!
It's an incredible
result for the Croydon karter.
While, for team-mate Ollie,
Cadwell has given him
another important lesson
about the roller-coaster of racing.
Yeah, I'm devastated.
Missed second gear out of the start.
Let the pressure get to me, maybe.
For the whole team,
this first race meeting has been
a massive step forward.
To keep the momentum going, a few
days later, I organise an outing.
The aim is to give the team
the inspiration they'll need to
push on as the stakes get higher.
The place is the home
of the McLaren Formula 1 team.
Is that Senna's car? Yeah.
This is one of the most successful
cars in race history.
For more than six decades,
McLaren has been
a leader in world motorsport.
James Hunt, Niki Lauda,
Senna, Hamilton,
all raced and won with McLaren.
If you want to be the best, you've
got to learn from
the absolute best, so I've got a
special guest for you to meet today.
Current McLaren F1 driver and
all-round superstar,
Lando Norris.
Oh, my gosh. Here he is!
Good morning.
We've got Callum, Lando.
Nice to meet you.
Lillie. Good to meet you, hello.
Hello. How are you?
Ollie. Nice to meet you, mate.
And Louis. All right?
They're our drivers.
These two keep the team alive,
these are the mechanics.
Fantastic. The important ones.
First of all, congrats,
I heard there was some silverware
from the weekend.
Yeah, thank you. Not bad, not bad.
Louis started in the karting,
that's where you started?
I did start karting. Karting's
probably the place you learn
most of your skills you
need for racing.
You don't have to do it, there's
a lot of drivers who didn't do it,
but karting's
one of the funnest as well.
They're posher than the ones
at bangers, aren't they? Yeah.
They're all plastic ones.
We should have brought yours,
stuck it in here, Louis.
Hide it in there,
no-one'll know. Yeah.
Your first F1 race, what
was going through your mind?
Oh, so much.
I was so nervous back then. Yeah.
Bit of a twitchy bum?
Oh, definitely, definitely!
A lot of it is just pressure
you put on yourself.
You know you'll be able to do well
if you just go out there
and do your job. You've done a race,
you've not done particularly well,
how do you shake that off?
You can't just do it yourself,
you've got to ask the people
who are there for you,
how can I do it better next time?
As soon as you've reviewed it,
you just kind of put it behind
and you look ahead to the next one.
And I believe you've got a
bit of something lined up
for all of our team today? I do.
So, two drivers coming with me,
we're going to have a
bit of session driving.
I was going to say,
when you say a bit a session,
these young people think you're
on about drinking.
It's a driving session,
not a drinking session.
And, Lillie and Callum, you're going
to be going with the engineers.
This is going to be mega today.
For Louis and Ollie, Lando
is going to be coaching them
on one of the most important tools
available to a modern racing driver.
Sim training is crucial. For me,
it's been a big part of my life.
Growing up, I spent a lot of
time on simulators.
Oh, look at this, lads.
Especially starting off, when you're
new into the world of racing
and you're learning different cars,
you're learning different tracks.
There's nothing new in F1 using
simulators for driving training.
What's really remarkable is that
home-gaming racing sims
are now also so accurate that teams
like McLaren are embracing them too.
In their dedicated eSports studio,
Lando has loaded up the Donington
circuit that Louis and Ollie
will be driving in the GT Cup.
And he's using a McLaren GT4 racer
to lay down a benchmark lap time.
Makes it look easy, don't he?
I know, yeah.
So, that was my lap.
My one lap.
A 1:38.520.
Not my best lap I've ever done
but it was pretty good.
I mean, you made that look quite
straightforward
but I'm pretty sure it's not.
Thank you. It's my job.
So, if you get around this lap time,
you'll be in a good place.
Deeper in the bowels of
the McLaren Technology Centre...
..Lillie and Callum are with
the F1 pit crew
for a unique look at the mechanic's
role at the very top of the game.
There's between two and six stops
over the race, normally.
So, this is where the mechanics can
make the difference between
winning a race and losing a race.
How the BLEEP are we going
to do that?
So, guys, that one was a 2.3,
that time.
So, yeah, over to you guys.
Back in the sim, Louis and Ollie are
chasing Lando's 1:38 lap time.
There are a few things which you can
just never feel in the sim.
One is fear. Yeah.
And also the G-force is the
one other thing which
you just don't feel. You don't feel
the physical attributes.
How much seat time on a sim
do you do a week?
A day at least on the simulator,
preparing for every weekend.
So, when you're stepping in,
instead of leaving this leg
back here, bring it in and use
your whole body to drive it home.
Nice work.
Nice work, guys.
Great job.
But their car control's good.
What do we have at the moment?
1:44, Ollie. 1:43?
1:43, Louis.
Which is not bad.
Adapting to a new car,
a quicker car than what they're
used to driving.
Good work, lads, good work.
The team's been given
a taste of the big leagues,
and have shown real spirit doing it.
It's the spirit they'll need
for this experiment's final test.
There's one last thing
I want to show you.
Because you've done amazing
in the MX-5s,
but Donington, different gravy.
I want to introduce you to the
car you're going to be driving.
Lando, if you'll do the
honours on that corner, pal.
570S GT4.
450hp, 3.8l,
north of 180mph.
I'm lost for words.
The MX-5s were brilliant,
and now we've gone the complete
opposite end.
Excitement, nerves,
the opportunity's amazing.
I can't believe I'm actually
going to drive it.
Just want to get out there,
do my best.
Yeah, I've got a new challenge.
They're a bit crazy for trusting
Ollie and Louis with it.
But I'm excited to see
how they get on with it.
Lando, thank you
so much for coming down today,
really appreciate you giving
up your time for us.
All right, go on, you lot, skedad.
Cheers, mate. Cheers.
The team has gathered for their
first chance to get to grips
with the new car on track.
A lot more at stake, a lot less
margin for error and a lot
more room for big mistakes,
big accidents and potentially
injuries, so it's a massive step up
from what they've done before.
The McLaren is a daunting
prospect for them all.
But while Lillie and Callum are now
supported by a bigger pit crew,
Louis and Ollie
will be on their own.
More pressure on the drivers.
We can't crash it, they can.
And first behind the wheel
of the £220,000 racer is Louis.
I think it's a bit of a reality
check, we've been talking about it,
we've been about driving a GT car,
now the guys are actually in a GT
car for the first time
and it's real.
The car looks an animal.
So, I'm looking forward,
a bit nervous.
When the guys get in these cars
for the first time,
there's always a lot of emotion
and overthinking going on.
And through the day,
they'll just iron that out.
So, we'll get there,
we'll work through with them.
Despite not being a whole
lot heavier, the McLaren is over
three times as powerful as the MX-5s
the lads have been racing.
The forces involved in just
driving it
prove to be a serious wake-up call.
My vision was going blurry.
Because of the G-force of braking
I'm not used to.
I thought the Mazda was bad,
this is just ten times worse.
Ollie, what do you reckon?
How did that feel? I didn't know
what I were doing, really.
Didn't know what you were doing?
No. No?
All that training, all that prep...
Yeah, it went out the window.
Went out the window, OK.
Just overwhelmed by the whole
experience? Yeah. Yeah?
In what way?
Everything, everything.
I want to start from scratch
and work my way back up.
Yeah.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
As experiments go, Pad,
that's a hefty one.
Talk about a wake-up call.
They knew it wasn't going
to be easy, but I don't think
they realised how tough
it was going to be.
A bunch of novices racing
in GT Cup in a McLaren?
That's in at the deep end, boss.
Yeah.
Me and Chris raced in that series
and let me tell you, it's proper.
Chris didn't even finish.
You broke the car! Bad workman.
Leave it, lads. We'll see...
What? Leave it!
We'll see whether our race team
can cut it in the big league
later on in the show.
But now, we must move on
to talk about hot hatches,
isn't that right, Christopher?
It is, Patrick.
And the hot hatch we need to talk
about is this one -
the Honda Civic Type R,
which, for a long time, has been
the most in-your-face hot hatch
of the lot, getting fightier and
angrier generation on generation.
And now, buckle up, because
there's a new one on the scene.
Well, here's a turn-up
for the books.
This is the new Honda Civic Type R
and in a break with tradition,
it doesn't look like it should be
wearing an ankle tag. In fact...
..the world's most thuggish
hot hatch
looks like it's gone a bit grown-up.
But fear not,
because under that sensible new
suit, the Civic Type R is still...
ENGINE REVS
TYRES SQUEAL
..an absolute delinquent!
It's got more power
than ever before.
324 horsepower from a two-litre
turbo-charged engine.
OK, that's only a few more
horsepower than the old one,
but it'll still do 170mph.
0-60 in five seconds.
I mean, how much more do you want?
That's immense
for a little hot hatchback.
And while more and more fast
hatchbacks are turning up
with sensible four-wheel drive
these days,
the Civic remains
defiantly old school.
Hot Hatches should, in my book,
be front wheel drive.
That's the whole point of them.
What's the upside?
Weight is the upside.
Probably 200kg less than
a four-wheel-drive equivalent.
TYRES SQUEAL
Look at this.
It's got a proper manual gearbox.
Third, second.
Honda are masters
at these manual shifts.
Describe this new one...
It is exceptionally rigid,
yet smooth,
and that is not remotely amusing.
And this car reminds us what a hot
hatch should be like inside.
It's basic. Not too much going on,
but the seat is just exquisite.
I think it's the best seat
I've ever sat, in a fast car.
I've got dials everywhere.
I've got Honda quality.
But it's not trying to be grown-up.
It's not trying to be a luxury car.
It shouts -
"Get in me and thrash me!"
Which isn't remotely amusing,
either.
What is amusing is just how much
work Honda has put in
to the bits
that no-one will ever notice.
They're very proud
of the turbocharger,
which is 3% more efficient.
Now, that might not sound like much
to you and I,
but to some Honda engineer,
that was four years of hard work.
Exhaust flow improved 13%.
Torsional rigidity improved 15%.
These are all tiny improvements,
but lumped together,
they result in a driving experience
that's just brighter and sharper
than ever before.
Just feels so alive.
A car that makes you smile.
Ha-ha-ha!
This reminds me
of being young and stupid.
In fact, there's only
one real issue here,
and it's not with the car.
Hot hatches are not designed
for big, open airfields.
They're about cross-country
point-to-point pace.
They're about B-roads.
But the trouble with B-roads is that
they come with real world problems
like speed limits and speed cameras
and other traffic.
Well, not any more.
Introducing the B-Road-a-Matic 3000
for when you simply must add
interest to your desolate airfield.
I know it may look like a tractor
with a couple of pots of paint
strapped to the back
but it's actually a very technical
piece of equipment
developed over many, many months,
and I'm extremely proud of it.
And with my very own B-road
now open for business,
it's time to release the Civic
back into its natural habitat.
Already it feels just right.
What a thing!
It's so impressive.
You'd swear it was four-wheel drive.
Pitch it in.
Just yobbery at its finest.
This is why these cars were made -
for these conditions. It's so agile.
The front of the car is just superb.
It's so obedient.
You just turn, it goes.
And best of all, I don't feel
totally ashamed driving it
because it wasn't styled
by a seven-year-old.
Honda has nailed it with this thing.
It's a proper hot hatch.
Hello-hello?
Look at this lot.
Hello. Andrew. To what do I owe this
pleasure? What a line-up.
I have assembled all these classic
hot hatches just to let you know
what they're all about.
But, firstly, what's that like?
Fantastic, mate.
They've smashed it out of the park.
Really, really good car.
It's a bit more subtle
than the last one.
Better to drive. It's wonderful.
I'm sure it's lovely to drive.
Is it a hot hatch? Well,
it's got a hatchback and it's hot.
But...
..it's massive.
You see, whether it's the classic
Citroen AX GT...
Honestly, you wouldn't believe
how agile and fast that is.
..the iconic
Renault Clio Williams...
Do you know what, when I was a kid,
we used to see the odd one of these
knocking about and you thought,
"I want one of these."
..the original VW Golf GTI...
When you think of the original hot
hatchback, the Golf is it, isn't it?
..or even the last truly
game-changing Civic Type R...
Now we're talking.
This moved the game on completely.
..what this line-up of greats
shows is that true hot hatches
all share the same simple,
lightweight, compact DNA.
It's a fantastic line-up, Fred,
I have to say, it makes me smile,
but also a bit wistful for the past
because, well, it makes you realise
how sort of big and bloated
things have become, really. Yeah.
Because the problem is, Fred,
all this old stuff is all very well
but you can't have an old-style
hot hatch that's new.
You can. You can have that.
No, you can't. You can.
You can thank me later.
Ladies and gentlemen, I give you
the new OLD Peugeot 205 GTI.
Oh-oh-oh!
It's the work of a British
company called Tolman.
You take an old 205 GTI,
strip it down to the bare bones,
and regenerate it
better than ever before.
This is what they call a Restomod.
And, yeah, we've seen
Restomods before,
but they've always been
unbelievably expensive.
This 205 is about 45 grand
and, don't get me wrong,
I know that that's a lot of cash,
but, at the same time, it's a
similar price to Chris' Civic.
And I've got to say,
this is a lot more special.
Tolman's gone to town
on every inch of this Peugeot.
The engine's
been totally overhauled.
There's stronger brakes,
new suspension.
They've even updated
the old interior.
OK, so what they didn't manage to do
was find any more space.
If you're my height, 6'4",
you're not exactly
sitting in the car.
I feel like I'm wearing it.
But I've got electric windows.
I've got power steering.
I've got a DAB radio!
And the real genius
is the Tolman 205 doesn't feel like
a new car in old clothes.
It's still shot through with
that classic hot hatch spirit.
Only got 130 horsepower,
which is less than your average
family car nowadays.
But I'm only shifting 900kg,
so it's light, it's nimble,
it's fun!
It is fun. What a car!
Chris, I'm so pleased
you came out to play.
Admit it, you're jealous.
It's absolutely stunning.
It's the perfect hot hatch shape.
Let's see what it can do.
Make it dance. Come on!
It's not particularly quick,
but it's nimble
and it is so much fun.
Oh, here we go.
Tell you what, Fred,
it looks so good I'm already sold.
Where do I write the cheque?
Look at it.
I've got to say, I wanted one
of these when I was about 20
and I've never driven one
up until today
and this thing is not disappointing.
I can't shake you off, though,
that is for sure.
I suppose I'd better demonstrate
where the progress is now.
Oh, ta-ra, Chris!
That's what 30 years does.
That is what it does.
The truth is, though,
there are no losers here.
Whether you fancy a lovingly-updated
classic or the very best that
modern engineering prowess can
produce, you can't really go wrong.
What we're saying is, then,
if you're into hot hatches,
it's a good time to be alive.
Happy days. Which reminds me,
I've got something to show you.
I've built a B-road!
Oh, it's perfect. Yes!
This is what this car was made for.
This is some road, Christopher.
Congratulations.
It's about smiles, not speed,
Andrew. Smiles, not speed.
Roundabout. Roundabout. Oh, yes.
Do you mind if I go again?
One more time.
What a car.
The Peugeot 205 GTI Tolman.
Thank you.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
That...
..is a really good car.
It is. So is that, though.
Do you know what,
seeing them both side by side,
it's amazing the size difference.
I mean, how the hell in the '80s,
did we fit in them?
Cos in the '80s, Paddy, we were
kids. We were smaller.
You were never that small. You're
like Donkey Kong in Mario Kart.
You driving around in one
of them is unbelievable.
So go on, then, Pad, fresh pair
of eyes on it, which one you having?
It's a tricky one because
17-year-old Pad would
have loved one of them. I get that.
On the other hand, 17-year-old Pad
would have loved one of them.
Similar prices?
Well, same ballpark.
Oh, it's a tricky one.
They're both so good.
I'm going to have to
go for the Civic. Yeah.
I'm going to have to go
for the Civic
but I'd pop the Peugeot in the boot
for a blast down memory lane
every now and again.
Perfect two-car garage.
Right, that's that sorted. Now we
must get back to our young race team
where things
were about to get really serious.
Just seven weeks since our young
team first came together,
this bold experiment
is reaching its conclusion.
A band of talented drivers
and mechanics
whose racing ambitions
could never have reached so far...
..are now going wheel-to-wheel
with a multimillion pound grid
of hardened racers in the GT Cup.
It's extremely tough. They really
have to soak up everything
that we say like a sponge, not get
overwhelmed by the whole experience.
From what we've seen of them
in the car so far,
you know, they're adapting to it
very, very well
and taking it on board very quickly.
It's pre-race practice.
Louis and Ollie have had two weeks
intensive training with the car
and now it's their last chance
to prepare.
We've got brand-new brakes
on the front...
30% brake pressure, 50%, 70.
The warm-up session doesn't
just give them the chance
to set the car up for the track,
it's also the driver's
one opportunity
to rehearse crucial moments
of the race to come.
I want you to practise
the driver chain
as they come into the pits hot.
Hit your marks on the board. Get out
the car as quick as can, Louis,
then you're jumping in,
waiting for the push back.
Remember, once the lollipop
releases you,
you've got to mash that throttle.
Full faith on him. You just got to
go into the fast lane and go.
For mechanics Lillie and Callum,
meanwhile,
working with the McLaren
has meant finding their place
in a professional pit crew.
Lillie and Callum have gelled well
with their team.
They get on with everybody.
They've stepped up to the next
level, checking suspension,
you know, we changed brakes
yesterday
and I think they'll do
really well today.
The whole team
has raised their game.
But as practice comes to an end,
the real test starts now.
Just, uh...
..keeping everything crossed.
We've got 20 minutes
and then we're out.
So the call for the tyres will be
a little bit earlier. Yeah. Yeah.
So I want you guys out. You got
gloves? I'll get some now. Yeah.
You want good ones. Yeah? Cos the
pull for the tyres will strain you.
All right. Yeah. Yeah?
You good? Yeah. Thank you.
The incredible field that makes up
the GT Cup grid
is divided into six
competitive categories.
Team Top Gear is competing
in the GTH class
against nine other McLarens,
Porsches and AMG Mercs.
As a team endurance event,
both drivers will have to
prove themselves.
First with the qualifying rounds.
On new tyres, low fuel,
he's going to get about three laps
to do a time.
My boy.
Yeah, he's my
little gentle giant.
I know he's in a really,
really fast car.
Yeah, my heart should be
palpitating.
But I've got confidence in him
and he's a confident lad as well.
Do you believe how mad it is
from karting to doing this?
I mean, it's mad, isn't it?
It is crazy.
Oh, I'm buzzing for you.
Buzzing for you.
I can't believe that my boy
is competing at this level.
I just couldn't be more proud.
The opportunity which he's had here
is something that's unobtainable
to the working man.
You can't afford to race a McLaren.
You can't afford to sit
in a McLaren.
Louis and Ollie's first-ever
competitive performance in the car
is enough to qualify them
8th in class.
And now the end of the road
for Team Top Gear
lies on the other side of
a 50-minute endurance race.
A race where each driver
gets a stint,
swapping midway
with a full team pit stop.
Competing right through to the
chequered flag would need them
ALL to be on their game.
Right, guys,
it's time to get serious now.
This whole journey is pointed
to the GT Cup race.
50-minute race.
I want Louis to start
and then for you, Ollie, to bring
home the chequered flag. Perfect.
Come on, lads. Let's do it.
I'm more nervous
watching this than...
I know, it's the thing, isn't it?
You just want them to be safe,
don't you? They're like your kids.
Our stomachs are in knots. Imagine
what their bloody dads are like.
Louis is approaching the end
of the formation lap,
and the rolling start
is just seconds away.
It's time to find out
how this team reacts
when he comes to the big moment.
Lights are on on the gantry.
They go out now.
And we get Round 20 of the 2022
Championship season under way
for GT Cup.
Come on! Come on, Louis!
It looks as though everybody
is safely through the first corner.
Louis came on the radio and says,
"The car in front
is slowing me down."
It takes a bit of skill,
a bit of experience.
So you've got to work out
where you are quicker during the lap
and then pick your moment.
Has he got him? Yeah, got him.
Pace is really good.
Faster than that car in front.
That car is running top three
in the points.
Louis is making his mark
as he claws away at the field.
All the while in the garage,
the team's pit stop strategy
is being calculated.
If he's got a bit of traffic,
we might get Ollie in to try
and do an undercut to try
and overtake during the pit stops.
Or if Louis is in clean air,
just keep him out there.
Just keep going.
Get yourself ready, warmed up.
Do something to me as well.
Out on track, the battles
and drama continue...
Whoa! Uh-oh! Oh!
..but Louis is holding his own.
There he is, there he is.
Go on, go on, go on, go on.
What do you think about his position
at the minute? You happy?
Yeah, he's doing a good job.
We're holding P7 right now.
So this is number 25 car...
Go on, Louis!
..going well in the hands of
Louis Smithen making his debut
in the Championship, scheduled
to hand the car over to Ollie Hall.
The pit stop window opens
and the team in the garage
get ready to go to work.
How long till he's in?
Three minutes.
Whatever happens, happens. Do your
best, that's all we can ask for.
Oh!
Go on, Ol.
Please confirm...
Let's do it.
Get out, go, go.
Here we go.
Where are we?
Go.
Good job, good job, good job.
What happened with
the safety car, then?
So, Car 17 crashed out.
Safety car came out just as
we were coming into the pit,
so I think that may have played
out in our favour.
How was it? It was fun.
So much fun, yeah.
You looked great out there.
I could hear you saying the guy
in front of you was slower.
You got past. Yeah. Oh!
Louis held 7th place
at the handover
and, as the safety car pits,
the race resumes. Here we go.
Ollie now has just over ten minutes
to bring it home for the team.
Go on!
Two more laps to go.
Go on, Ol, push!
Come on, Ollie, bring it home, son.
Bring it home.
Yes! Yeah, boy.
Good lad.
Well done, lad.
P7. Well done, mate.
Good job. Thank you.
Fantastic. Fantastic.
Well done. You believe that?
No. Can you believe that? Eh?
Yes, come on, Ollie!
CHEERING
Yes. Oh, mate!
Few beers tonight?
Oh, that was just probably
the best day of my life.
I'm just so happy that we got
a good result for the team.
Yeah, I'm just amazed.
Wow, it's been incredible. We didn't
start out as racing drivers,
but we've definitely finished
as one.
It's been so incredible.
It's like something
you're never going to forget,
being here, doing all of this.
The paddock team
has just been amazing.
I just want to thank them
so much for looking after me.
The mechanics, especially,
for getting the car set up for me.
Callum and Lillie, me two mechanics,
we have been on a journey.
We've got some amazing memories
together
and memories
that we'll cherish forever.
It's just been amazing
from start to finish.
The dream for me is basically to do
what I've done the last couple
of months, just as a living.
The dream for the future will be to
continue in any form of motorsport.
There we go.
A couple of months ago,
we had an idea.
Could we get four young people
together and get into racing,
people who would never get a shot?
And if we could, what would happen?
There's your answer.
And it just goes to show
the talent's out there.
All they need is a chance.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Give it up for Lillie,
Callum, Ollie and Louis!
Amazing. Respect to all of you.
Eight weeks from a standing start
to racing in GT Cup,
that is a hell of an effort.
Fantastic.
I tell you what, when that flag
dropped at Donington,
all the nerves kicked in.
For me, it was like sending
your kids off to school
for the first time,
but this time the kids are driving
220-grand McLarens!
And I'll tell you what else.
After only two months on the job,
they've already done better than us.
They've actually managed to finish
a race without breaking down
or smashing up a car.
Well done. Amazing.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
And it goes to prove that there's
real talent out there
and I'm very proud
of that young team.
Ladies and gentlemen,
give it up for Team Top Gear!
CHEERING
Again! You're milking it now.
Milking it.
And that's it for us tonight
and for the next few weeks,
because we're off your screens
for something called the World Cup.
Come on, England!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
And Wales!
Thanks so much for watching.
See you in a few weeks. Goodnight.