[opening theme music playing]
WHEN LIFE GIVES YOU TANGERINES
[waves crashing]
THE BLAZING SUMMER SUNSHINE
[woman] It's so hot today.
Wow, it's scorching hot.
Perfect weather to torment
your daughter-in-law.
They say 108 prostrations
should be enough.
[button clicks]
It would've worked already
if 108 were enough.
She's wasted five years.
Even Buddha's sick after 3,000.
- Suffering yields dedication.
- [woman] You're just mean. Just mean.
How can a lady of the house be so cruel
and expect more children from her?
[Gye-ok] Let's be honest.
Not all children survive.
You could have eight, and two might die.
If the family she married into
valued sons, huh,
she should be having plenty.
How could she try to freeload
off our family?
Her family didn't give us a single
silver spoon as dowry. Nothing at all.
[Mak-cheon] What about you?
Did you bring us a silver spoon?
Is that why you had two?
You can't stand me, but your
granddaughter-in-law is precious, huh?
Let's go now, Ae-sun.
[groans] If you make her do
3,000 prostrations,
she'll be too exhausted to do housework.
[Gye-ok] Yes, she does so much,
doesn't she?
That'll be your pillow talk, huh?
Go ahead, tell your husband
I made you do 3,000.
He could take your side right away,
but no husband likes
when his wife bad-mouths his mother.
Huh?
You know, the biggest mama's boys
really want their wives to be
the most devoted daughters-in-law.
So watch what you say, huh?
[groans] Was that directed to my ears?
Fine, I won't say anything.
Sure you wouldn't.
And, plus, he groans in pain each night.
I don't wanna give him
more reasons to be upset.
[Gye-ok scoffs] Well, good for you.
They say a man
stays with a wife he loves
despite despising her family.
For me, it's the opposite.
[Gye-ok] How dare you?
Serves you right. [chuckles]
Seems my granddaughter-in-law's
bested my daughter-in-law.
[Gye-ok] Oh, she's so annoying.
Should I teach her a lesson?
Hey, why did you just hit
the hareubang's nose?
Huh? Hey.
Why did you just hit his nose? Huh?
Oh, uh, I'm sorry.
Stop right there!
YEOM SUN-NAM, YEOM SUN-BONG
Even the government says
only having one child is patriotic.
They keep saying sons though.
Who cares if we birth sons anyhow?
What was gained by raising Gwan-sik, huh?
They did all that just to give him to me.
Why did she keep throwing red beans at us?
Who cares if my mom's spirit
is still here?
So what if my mom wants to visit me?
So what?
[sighs]
[wistful piano music playing]
I can't even visit my mom's house now.
Well, that's not right.
I do miss her more now that I'm a mom.
I miss my mom even more.
[clattering]
[sniffles]
[sighs]
Honestly, must be upsetting
to not be permitted
to visit this house anymore.
[Gye-ok] Mmm.
Mmm.
Ooh! Oh.
[Gyeong-ja] You can keep bringing her,
but we're not going to accept her.
We're not taking in new people.
She's so young.
Why do you always drag her here?
Veteran haenyeo start their training
between six and seven.
Who begins haenyeo work at the age of six?
Children her age pick kelp
in the shallow waters.
That's why.
I heard that this spot's for beginners,
so you make her go play in the water now
so she won't be so afraid of it later,
you know?
- She your daughter?
- Mm.
Oh, I don't even want to talk to you now.
All right?
And does Ae-sun know?
Did you ask if it's all right?
Why do I have to get permission?
She can't control me.
Horses and people
must prove their worth to make a living.
We want her to learn a skill.
Why would you be against her having that?
Mak-cheon, listen to me.
Every time we go back into the water,
we ask God, "Don't let us die, Lord."
That's why Gwang-rye
told Ae-sun every day,
"Don't become a haenyeo.
Please don't bother learning to dive."
If Gwang-rye didn't want
her daughter doing it,
she wouldn't want
her granddaughter to do it.
You responsible for keeping
Geum-myeong alive?
Stop nagging and let her dive.
You better mind your own business, ladies.
I'm done.
[melodic music playing]
[Gye-ok] Oh gosh.
- [Gyeong-ja] Here.
- [Gye-ok] Oh my.
[grunts]
[Gye-ok] Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. My goodness.
Well, damn it!
I envy people with daughters!
Wonder how many they'll have?
Who's to blame when you're destined
to live as a housekeeper?
They have two weeks left to pack,
so why are you packing for them?
Don't they have hands?
How will you live now that those brats
won't be around anymore?
[Ae-sun] Hey, they're not brats,
and I get angry quick.
- Also, my in-laws…
- Yes, yes.
I know their influence reaches
the Jeju provincial office.
You've told me countless times
that they have sway over lawmakers here.
But does their influence extend
all the way to the mainland?
I'm saying I stand with those kids.
So don't be mean to Sun-nam and Sun-bong
and give them plenty of food to eat.
What if I'm mean, then?
I wanna be tough on them sometimes,
but it's pretty difficult.
How can I when they call me "Mom, Mom"?
After raising kids in your house
for ten years, they get to be yours,
even if they're not.
What matters more than blood is the heart.
[sighs] You still can't figure that out?
Gimme.
[baby coos]
I'm… sure you have plenty
to be angry about with no one to talk to.
Give me a call.
Maybe you wanna trash-talk
the hag that throws beans at you.
I'll listen to you.
[scoffs] You know
we're not friends like that, right?
[Min-ok sighs]
Honestly, I wasn't a mistress.
I didn't steal him from her.
We got married ten years
after she passed away.
There's no need for enmity.
You and I aren't meant
to be friends though.
Oh, is that why you had to run away
with my yellow dress that night?
[scoffs] I'm just not your friend.
I do respect you.
Now that I've lived in this household,
I respect you.
You're not destined to be a housekeeper.
You just have the heart of one.
So then,
stick with your man.
You said he's a good guy.
[gentle piano music playing]
Mm, then I…
What?
…guess…
Um, I guess…
What?
- Spill it.
- I guess I can entrust them to you.
My siblings.
- Please let them…
- What?
…finish school.
Stop worrying about my children.
Quit it.
Yeah, but still,
I wouldn't just get four popsicles
like you did back then.
So if I get corn,
then I do get five, okay?
I'm giving you this tricycle instead of
popsicles.
Just think of it as a moral
school grant that I'm donating
to Geum-myeong, okay?
Hand out a used tricycle
as a school grant. Really?
After the time you sacrificed for this
family, you're only stealing the tricycle?
What do you mean by "steal" exactly?
You told me to take it.
[music playing on TV]
[woman on TV] One well-raised daughter
is better than ten sons.
[man on TV] Planned Parenthood Federation
of Korea.
[Gye-ok groans]
She took the corn again today.
This time, I counted how many cobs we had.
We have a thief in our own home
when we don't even have enough for us.
It's not like she has parents to support,
so why does she give
the little we have left
to people who are barely family to her?
There's tilefish inside.
You brought tilefish?
Tilefish
for the corn cobs.
Do you only care about your wife,
or what is it?
Who's gonna take my side if my only boy
keeps on prioritizing his wife's side?
Dad's supposed to be taking your side.
What are you looking at?
I can't look at my own husband?
Uh, no.
I should've raised some dogs instead.
Hey, you stole the corn cobs
from the cauldron.
Wow, Ae-sun, are you a refugee now?
I gave them five corn cobs, you see?
And brought all of these.
[pants]
Look at that. [giggles]
[Gye-ok] Oh, is this real?
[gasps]
Why did you bring this one?
Wearing this to go back to Busan?
Throw red beans at them. Red beans.
Some of the clothing
that they used to wear
are very nearly new, really.
You know, honestly, she could've given
the tricycle to her own baby,
but instead,
she just gave it to Geum-myeong.
[chuckles]
Throw the tricycle away.
Girls shouldn't ride tricycles.
If my husband were alive,
his pipe would've smacked you already.
If a peddler shows up,
we'll barter the tricycle for taffy.
[sighs]
[Ae-sun] Geum-myeong,
did you go play by the sea today?
Geum-myeong, it's bedtime.
Uh, going to bed already?
She goes to sleep early.
Good night.
[Gye-ok] Good night.
[Gwan-sik] Sleep well.
Hope you won't be as grouchy.
[gentle music playing]
COLLEGE ENTRANCE EXAM
PREPARATION WORKBOOK 1
OH AE-SUN
GENERAL EQUIVALENCY DIPLOMA
NAME: OH AE-SUN
[music fades]
[Gwan-sik] Where have you been?
[Ae-sun sighs]
I just love red beans so much.
[sighs]
You worn out?
Should I just keep my trap shut?
If you take my side,
it won't simply be hate.
They will want to kill me as well.
How can I help you?
[sighs]
Let me try, huh?
I'd rather be the bad guy
if you'll let me.
The tricycle.
Let Geum-myeong ride the tricycle.
Geum-myeong has to be
able to ride it. Really.
Really?
If she can't even ride a tricycle,
she'll just live in the kitchen
the rest of her days.
I want Geum-myeong
to have everything, Gwan-sik.
For her to have it all and do anything.
I want… I want her to prosper in life.
I don't want her to set the table forever.
I want her to flip the table over instead.
You flip it too.
If you flip it,
I will clean the whole thing up.
[sobs]
It's so frustrating.
You can flip it or break it.
You just tell me when,
and they'll take it out on me.
Okay? I'll make sure
they know their limits.
And, plus, they've been on me
for stealing fish to give you.
- When?
- What?
When, I said.
I said when.
[melodic pop music playing]
[Mak-cheon] Grant her a son.
Bless her womb.
Please bless her womb with a boy.
Grant her a son.
Grant her a son, I beg you.
Bless her womb.
Please.
Bless her womb with a boy.
Please grant her a boy.
[yawns]
Grant her a son.
Grant her a son, I beg you.
Down.
You better not tell Gwan-sik
that I've been throwing red beans at you
first thing every morning.
A talkative wife is no good anywhere.
[yawning]
A woman who speaks a lot
and is lazy is useless.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hmm.
Ah no!
How many times do I have to tell you
not to mix the peas like that?
- Good God!
- [Geum-myeong] She told him when.
- Mom's morning started like any other day.
- [Gye-ok] Jeez.
Though she was confined
to a small treadwheel…
she found
the small joys in life every day.
[Mak-cheon sighs]
[Gwan-sik] It was 2,000 won.
If you want 2,000 won
worth of taffy, do it.
[Gye-ok scoffs]
You're smiling?
Peas, I want some peas, Mommy.
Peas, oh, here.
Peas. I want peas, please.
[Ae-sun] Where are the peas?
Where are they?
[young Geum-myeong] Huh?
[gentle music playing]
- I wanna eat at this table from now on.
- Why?
You insolent son.
I'd like
to eat with my mom at this table.
[Gye-ok] Dogs are better. Dogs.
[young Geum-myeong] Peas.
We bought some peas, Mommy.
[Mak-cheon] Be careful.
[Gye-ok] Look, she's doing it. She's okay.
CATCH A SPY
BRING HONOR TO THE FAMILY
Grant me a grandbaby.
A grandson. Please send a grandson.
Why not put her in a princess carriage?
That tricycle's a waste of money.
You should've spent it on something else.
I'm heading out.
Be careful at sea.
[Ae-sun] Babe.
[Geum-myeong] With a smile on her face,
as always,
Ae-sun was spending
all her twenties in the tiny kitchen.
[Ae-sun] If she can't even
ride a tricycle,
she'll just live in the kitchen
the rest of her days.
I want Geum-myeong to have everything.
For her to have it all and do anything.
I want… I want her to prosper in life.
[music fades]
[sighs]
Oh.
Oh my.
Hey, are you a centipede?
[middle-aged Ae-sun] Goodness!
You'd never get to wear all of these.
When will she ever get
to wear all these shoes?
[sighs]
Are you opening a shoe store?
So then, I'd say,
just live with your mother.
She said she likes her plants indoors.
[sighs]
[gentle piano music playing]
[Geum-myeong sighs]
Your parents must've worked
so hard to send you to school
with their limited means.
They must be overjoyed
that you and Yeong-beom are dating.
Yes. [chuckles]
- They are excited.
- I'm sure they are.
Of course they are.
So you just got a job?
Uh, uh, yes.
The management
says a lot of nice things about me.
They say I'll be promoted really quickly.
So you'll keep working?
Huh?
You want to keep working
after you get married?
Uh…
- Yeong-beom and I…
- [silverware clatters]
Um, he and I, we talked about it already.
Listen,
greed is a result of wanting approval.
That desire turns to conceit.
People who come into wealth quickly
often feel the urge to show their riches.
It's funny when women marry into wealth
and start dressing in luxury clothes.
[chuckles]
What? Have I offended you?
[Geum-myeong sighs]
Let me be frank now.
Would you rather be promoted to manager
or be the next
vice minister's daughter-in-law?
Yeong-beom is our eldest son,
and he's very capable.
So then why would his wife
need a life outside the home
instead of supporting him?
It frustrates you
that I am old-fashioned?
The thing is…
I never want Geum-myeong
to feel inferior to anybody, anywhere.
I'm as capable as Yeong-beom is, and I…
I'm also my family's eldest child.
I want to take care of my family
with my own money.
And…
[sighs]
…I have a strong drive,
so just getting hired isn't enough.
I want to be the manager, supervisor,
and even president. I want it all.
That can't be a shameful ambition,
uh, isn't that true?
You're right.
I would think
that pretty girls would be more ladylike.
They say indoor plants
are a bit easier to manage.
[Geum-myeong sighs]
So what you mean is…
is you're not an indoor plant either?
- [silverware clatters]
- [sighs]
What can I do?
Apparently, I'm the not-pretty,
hard-to-handle eldest daughter.
I've had enough, okay?
I'm totally fine living without you,
and I'm not desperate
to get married either.
[sighs, moans]
[sighs]
[middle-aged Ae-sun] Good grief.
You have more shoes
than I've ever worn in my life.
Goodness, you make money to use like this?
I didn't ask you to clean them.
It's so cold, and that's all you wanna do?
They're all cheap shoes.
They aren't worth your money.
Goodness gracious.
Why did you buy so many shoes, huh?
This is all vanity
and a… waste of money.
Someone told me greed is conceit.
What's that?
Maybe because I grew up poor,
I want to keep buying more.
Maybe it's from deep pain.
[sighs] You made me beg,
sometimes for three days, if I wanted
new clothes for field trips, you know.
I wanted things, but we didn't have money.
I grew up wanting stuff so bad,
and we couldn't ever get it.
Now I never stop myself.
It's very much cheap stuff.
They're all impulse buys.
[window rattles]
[sighs]
It's not like I got what I liked
refusing to buy you what you wanted.
I still provided
the best food and clothing
I could give you with what we had.
What are you justifying right now?
You had me beg for things.
Did something ha… happen today
at the office?
Damn it!
Anyone giving you trouble?
You wouldn't understand, would you?
If you feel burned out,
then take time off.
A break would be good.
You work in an office building
and try to get a break.
If it's so hard,
then quit and get married…
And what?
You want me to live like you?
Get hitched into another poor family,
scraping by, spending my life…
[exhales]
[Geum-myeong] Breaking Mom's heart
broke my own heart just the same.
You're right. Yeah, you're right.
Don't live my life over.
[pensive music playing]
But, you know…
[sentimental music playing]
…I found happiness in my own way.
There was sunshine in my life too.
I've had so many picturesque moments.
[Ae-sun chuckles]
I'm asking you to recognize
that my life was worth living.
Mm-hmm.
- [Geum-myeong] It's an odd thing.
- [sighs]
Just give me the whole box. All of it.
Oh, okay.
[Geum-myeong] Parents get upset about
what they can't do for their kids.
Children get upset about
what their parents couldn't do for them.
Ae-sun, pay your respects.
Really?
Mm.
[Geum-myeong] But I had no clue
that my impoverished childhood…
[Mak-cheon] Her great-grandmother
may be a shaman,
but she needs her mother's blessings.
Nothing beats
a mother's dedication to her child.
…my hunger-ridden youth
was a fortress for which
they fought so fiercely.
There is no better job in Jeju
than being a haenyeo.
If we have one in the family,
she will then be our foundation.
She won't need to ask us for a thing.
She'll make her own money,
and as the eldest daughter,
she'll support the family.
[uneasy music playing]
[Mak-cheon] You can't expect a girl
to become a public official.
She won't become a judge or an attorney.
Becoming a haenyeo is her best option.
[loud clattering]
- Oh!
- [Mak-cheon] What?
W… what have you done?
- Oh, oh my. That… that girl… Oh, oh my.
- What in the…
She's my daughter!
She's not at the bottom
of the ladder in this house.
She's my daughter!
[dramatic music playing]
- How dare you!
- My daughter won't be a haenyeo.
She'll never be one.
[gasping, spluttering]
Have you lost your mind?
Where are you taking her?
[Mak-cheon] Oh my.
My mother developed a condition
because of her diving that killed her.
Till the day she died,
she said, "Don't be a haenyeo."
"Don't be a housekeeper."
- Because… because I live as a housekeeper.
- How dare you!
- Oh, Geum-myeong.
- A housekeeper, huh?
You call serving your in-laws
and our ancestors housekeeping?
You think I will let her
live like me as a housekeeper?
- My daughter won't live my life here.
- You will be grateful for your life here.
[Gye-ok] How dare you take a daughter
of the Yang family?
She's my daughter. Mine!
If you want a haenyeo in the family,
have your daughter do it. Why my daughter?
- [gasps]
- [music fades]
- [young Geum-myeong cries]
- [high-pitched tone]
[Mak-cheon] Oh, she lost her mind.
[Gye-ok] How dare you look me in the eye
and raise your voice at me!
"If you want a haenyeo,
have your daughter do it"?
Oh, god of the saints and god of the sea,
watch over us. Watch over us.
"Have your daughter do it"?
How dare you utter such nonsense!
You must be out of your damn mind.
I told you. I warned you.
Her mother's soul is in her.
Her spirit has possessed that girl.
- And that's why she's lost her mind.
- [Gye-ok] You're right!
That's what's happening.
Of course she acts just like her mother.
You grew up in a worthless household,
raised by a lowly woman.
This is an honorable household.
[Mak-cheon] Please watch over us.
- Please watch…
- Hey, Gwan-sik.
Did you see how she's been behaving?
Did you see her demeanor?
She says Geum-myeong isn't my grandchild
and disrespected the ancestors and glared
and kept screaming at me and just…
Say no more. Kick her out!
The ancestors will not tolerate her!
Grandma, have you been
throwing beans at her?
Kick her out of here!
Kick her out! Kick her out! Kick her out!
I hadn't hit her ever before.
[Mak-cheon] Oh dear.
This is just too much.
I can't breathe now.
- Oh no.
- Oh!
Oh no. Oh no. Mom!
Ae-sun, you're giving her a heart attack.
Oh my. Oh my.
[Gwan-sik] Mom. Grandma.
I'm the reason Ae-sun came here.
Not to be your daughter-in-law.
- What?
- [Gwan-sik] You won't see…
You won't see Ae-sun anymore.
I won't let her live here.
[Mak-cheon scoffs] How dare she!
Kick her out!
Oh my!
Why don't you wear them?
They suit you better, I think.
They fit really well, yes.
[chuckles]
Jeez, um,
you should've married a rich guy.
Then you could be all dressed up
in floral patterns all the time.
You do have some regrets, right?
If you told me to, uh,
go back and marry your dad again, I'd say…
Of course, you wouldn't.
Yeah.
I'd do it.
[sentimental music playing]
- [middle-aged Gwan-sik] Geum-myeong.
- Oh.
What's this?
Hey there.
[middle-aged Ae-sun] Oh, I told you
not to buy two bags.
Didn't I say that?
She can buy her own peas, you know?
What did you pay?
- You get scammed again?
- Look, I brought a whistle.
- [whistle blows]
- Oh, it's so loud!
- World's scary. [laughs]
- Look, babe. My shoes.
- Aren't they cute?
- Oh, they look good.
[laughs]
- Yeah.
- They fit great.
They look perfect.
DODONG-RI VARIETY SHOP
ONE ROOM, ONE KITCHEN
MONTHLY RENT, NO DEPOSIT NEEDED
[soothing pop music playing]
GA, NA, DA, RA…
- [Ae-sun] Geum-myeong, you want some peas?
- [young Geum-myeong] I want some peas.
[Ae-sun giggles]
One more time. Here are some peas.
- [young Geum-myeong] Here are some peas.
- Good. Eat some more.
One more time. You want some peas?
- [young Geum-myeong] I want some peas.
- Yes!
My darling.
- [young Geum-myeong] Squid. Squid.
- [Ae-sun] Squid? You want some squid?
[both] Squid.
[blowing]
Squid, squid. Oh.
- That's a good girl.
- Is it good? Is it good? [chuckles]
[man clears throat]
[whispers] Landlord. Landlord.
Hey, not those. Auntie gave them to us.
Won't he ask why we've got
abalone to eat when we can't pay rent?
[landlord clears throat]
Yes, sir!
Oh. [chuckles]
Sir, I, uh,
I am looking for
a new fishing job right now.
Could we pay rent
at the very end of the month?
Just pay me in the fall if that's better!
No, that's not it. I'm not implying
we're trying to scam you, okay?
Sir, hello.
I'll watch the store
more often if you like.
Someone came during the day
and handed me your rent for three months.
And you… you weren't aware of that?
Huh? Who did?
Someone handed you three months of rent?
Is there anyone named Do in your family?
Do you have a relative named Do?
Someone from the Do family paid for it.
So if you pay the rent on time,
I'll give you pork.
[landlord clears throat]
DO HUI-JEONG SCHOLARSHIP
AMOUNT: 10,000 WON
[pensive music playing]
[breathes deeply]
Stop glaring at me.
Who is she?
Who's Hui-jeong?
What? I've been side by side
with you since you were ten.
Really? Hui-jeong?
Mm, yeah. Nobody ever had a thing for you.
- Tell me how you're so sure.
- [scoffs]
I've never known anyone
from the Do family.
What about your grandma?
My grandmother's name is Kim Chun-ok.
My aunt's name is Hyeon Yi-suk.
Most importantly,
my grandmother is really poor.
My grandma is Park Mak-cheon.
My mom is Kwon Gye-ok.
It could be Mom.
Maybe my mom went into
the body of a rich housewife,
and she had her dip into her account
at the bank and then…
[jaunty music playing]
[clears throat]
[sighs]
[groans]
[jaunty music continues]
[sighs]
[landlord grunts] Oh, come on.
Oh, come on!
Why are they so inconsiderate?
How dare they!
[Gye-ok] Your landlady said
you guys get busy
as soon as it's 9:00 p.m.
At your age, yeah, I guess
you would be diligent in that, huh?
If you're so diligent about
turning off the lights at night,
of course
the goddess of fertility would bless you.
[woman 6 laughs] Look how happy she is
since leaving the in-laws.
Hmm? Living without stress
helps with pregnancy too.
[Gye-ok] If her in-laws tormented her
all day, and he walked into their room,
she wouldn't want to make love
to her mother-in-law's son.
[woman 6] Oh, of course
she wouldn't want to
make love to him then.
[woman 5 laughing] They're diligent, sure,
but the one I'm most proud of is…
[chuckles]
…Geum-myeong.
Oh, yes. What a gift you are.
Living in that tiny room.
[woman 6] My goodness gracious.
As long as they want them,
then a one-bedroom house
can support six kids, I think.
- [sighs, chuckles]
- [woman 6] Oh my. Oh my.
She's turning into Gwang-rye already.
This bookworm of a girl
is now a middle-aged woman. Jeez.
If you lived closer, we'd see you
as much as we used to see Gwang-rye.
You came all the way back here
just because your rent is a lot less?
[Gye-ok] Leave her alone.
If she lived here, her mother-in-law
would be over here all the time.
[woman 6] It's easier to make money
if you know folks.
Newbies aren't liked by islanders.
Hey, how's Gwan-sik's fishing job?
[Ae-sun] Well, he's hard-working,
as you know.
He hasn't told you
what it is he does, has he?
- You, you, you, you, watch your mouth.
- [Geong-ja] She needs to know though.
Why? What is it?
Gwan-sik hasn't said for whom he works?
Hey, is your hand okay?
- [Gyeong-ja] Oh!
- Oh no!
What's this?
- What happened to your hand?
- It's fine.
[sobs]
[man] You should've come
as soon as you got hurt.
If you wait too long,
your fingers won't heal right.
Big dummy. You said nothing.
If you were hurt, you should've asked them
to turn back to shore.
What's so glorious about fishing that
you'd pull the net and break your fingers?
[Ae-sun sighs]
[Ae-sun groans]
Cat got your tongue or what?
[woman 6] Life itself isn't evil,
but money is.
Unfortunately, that family has control
over the seas on this side of the island.
You can't get fishing work in Dodong-ri
and not work for that guy.
That's why he works for that guy.
[woman 6] You don't know.
He's young, but he's trying to be
the head of his household.
[sighs]
[gentle acoustic guitar music playing]
[Ae-sun grunts]
[sighs]
Hey, babe.
Honey!
Hey, can you not hear me?
Hey, help me get this inside.
Oh man.
[music fades]
Asleep without dinner again.
[breathing heavily]
Here you go. Right there.
Dad's a baby. He sleeps all day like one.
Sweetie.
Oh my.
It's hot.
You should change, right?
[Gwan-sik moans]
Oh.
You keep wearing long sleeves.
[Gwan-sik moans]
[gasps]
[Ae-sun gasps]
[pensive music playing]
Do you need to be on that squid boat?
You know, a man needs his rest.
Dad, bring us a hundred squids, okay?
Dad doesn't need to bring any squids back.
I will
bring so many squids for you.
[giggles]
Hey, babe!
[gentle piano music playing]
Catch a lot of fish!
Catch so many squids for me!
[chuckles]
- [Ae-sun] Go.
- Go.
[sighs]
[gentle piano music continues]
[young Geum-myeong] It looks yummy.
CREAMER - INSTANT COFFEE
[landlord groans]
You only get up to four for free.
I think I'll get another can of sugar.
- [boy 1] How dare you!
- [boy 2] How dare you!
[boy 1] Die!
- [boy 2] Why would I die?
- [boy 1] How dare you!
- [boy 2] Ah!
- How dare you! How dare you!
You dare challenge your older brother?
How dare you! How dare you!
- You really want to fight me?
- [boy 2] Ah-ha!
I… I didn't get to bring you kimchi
or visit when you were moving,
so I wanted to say hi today.
How are his fingers doing?
Are they healing all right, Ae-sun?
He's… [chuckles] …getting acupuncture.
Ah.
I nagged at my husband a little.
If a man was hurt,
he should've turned the boat around.
As if squids
are more important than people.
Mr. Kim and Mr. Park
asked him to turn the boat around.
They happened to have full nets that day.
I understand why
my husband got a bit greedy.
- [tender piano music playing]
- [sighs]
Mr. Yang is something else though,
isn't he?
How did he stay on that boat
overnight with those fingers?
If it were me, I would've been
rolling on the floor in pain.
So the captain
didn't turn the boat around?
Sorry?
He didn't turn the boat around?
Oh…
My husband can't open his hand fully now.
He moans in pain each night too.
You don't need to worry about that.
I did ask again and again
for my husband to quit hitting Mr. Yang,
so he, uh, he says he's really stopped
beating him up.
I don't know why
he's particularly mean to Mr. Yang.
My husband does have a temper,
but he's not a bad guy, you know.
[boy 1] How dare you!
[boys grunting]
[boy 1] You wanna mess with me?
I'll knock some sense into you!
[boy 2] How dare you!
How dare you! How dare you! Damn it!
How dare you!
[man 1] How dare you!
You wanna mess with me, huh?
You always leave so early.
You're a big deal?
That man can't ever wait to go home.
You always bring packed lunches.
What's packed in that bag, huh?
Goodbye.
Hey, asshole!
- You're driving the boat.
- [man 2] Oh, come on, Captain.
Do you have a crush on Gwan-sik?
Why hold back a man who wants to go home?
I'm gonna drink a box of booze,
so just stand by and drive this damn boat.
But, uh, Captain, he lives so close by.
Hey, man, listen!
If the captain doesn't get off the boat,
then no one gets off the boat either.
Supporting the captain is also
an element of working here, okay?
Get it?
Know what I'm saying?
Okay, let's get to work.
Let's get to work.
Now.
[liquid pouring]
Don't feel like it?
Wanna mess with me?
Tell me if you're not pleased
about what I said.
Please speak up
and buy your own boat, kid.
Oh, really? So what was it you said again?
"Shut up, man"?
[breathes deeply]
Ms. Park, don't justify
everything he does.
Yes, life is tough.
Still, I think
what isn't right isn't right.
[captain] Look, if you don't want to,
just say so.
You a mute or what, Gwan-sik?
Oh. Because you don't have a boat, right?
All right. All right, all right, I see.
No, I don't want to.
What?
I can't lie about wanting to.
[pensive music playing]
Hey!
[woman] Excuse me.
Oh.
[woman sighs]
[door opens and closes]
Just can't wait to get home, huh?
[music fades]
Why are you taking my squids?
You can't be taking these
except if I let you. Get that?
What boat do you own?
You can have these if I let you.
You can stay back if I say so.
Why are you always leaving early? Why?
What, do you like your wife that much?
What's there to like? What?
Say something. Why don't you tell me?
Are you crazy for her?
You passionate every night, huh?
Are you just dying to see her, are you?
Yes.
I'm dying to see her.
What?
[chuckles, scoffs]
You bunch of losers.
Gosh, you are such a punk.
Seriously, man. Really?
What? You don't know?
How dare you! How dare you, kid!
And why don't you ever
wanna go home, Captain?
- What'd you say?
- What?
Do you feel lonely there?
Because she doesn't treat you
the way you like?
[chuckles] Oh jeez.
[laughing]
Oh shit.
[breathing heavily]
That asshole.
[captain] You punks need me
to beat some sense into you?
Do you?
You asshole!
- Asshole!
- [upbeat jaunty music playing]
[young Ae-sun] Asshole!
[Ae-sun screaming]
Hey, you asshole!
You asshole!
[Geum-myeong] Dad always said
Mom wasn't really like a rose
but more like a whistle.
[Ae-sun panting]
[music fades]
[panting]
Gwan-sik won't work… for you
ever again.
He's done working for you!
'Kay, don't do it.
Go away, man, just go home.
My brother's the chief
of the fishing village.
Don't think about getting
on a boat in Dodong-ri again!
Boy, I dodged a bullet on that one.
Asshole!
That girl, how dare she!
The little brat! Reckless.
The husband and the wife are equally bad.
[spits]
- Take this!
- [captain grunts]
- [captain groans]
- You need me to beat some sense into you?
Why you little…
How dare you!
Huh?
You should come to your senses first,
and then we'll see…
we'll see…
we'll see who really dodged a bullet here…
How dare you!
[captain] You wench!
[whimpers] Ouch!
Sang-gil's nickname needs a change.
Dodong-ri's asshole.
Yeah, "Asshole!"
- [laughs]
- [Sang-gil groans]
Oh man. Oh, that hurts so much.
[gentle piano music playing]
[sniffles]
A whistle. A whistle.
You're a human whistle.
[crying]
You kicked him. Why are you crying?
[crying continues]
[middle-aged Ae-sun] We don't need
a water heater. It doesn't use coal.
What about the draft?
You said if you could do it,
you'd do it all over,
and you'd marry me again.
[Geum-myeong] Mom always said…
- Would you?
- Why would I?
I'm fed up with you.
[Geum-myeong] …out of all of us,
Dad's the one who pains her the most.
[middle-aged Ae-sun]
Steel wears out too, doesn't it?
Why is your body already breaking down?
Stop scaring me, okay?
[middle-aged Gwan-sik] Oh my.
You've been lifting big loads
since you were ten.
Of course you're having issues.
Don't worry, Ae-sun.
I'm going to outlive you anyway.
What? When I die,
would you want another wife?
[tender pop music playing]
Would you like a new wife?
I couldn't treat you like that.
I don't want someone to replace you.
I'd feel better sending you off first
and then following after.
[tender pop music continues]
"THE SAME SKY, THE SAME STARS,
ETCHED IN THE SAME HEARTS."
[music fades]