WHEN LIFE GIVES YOU TANGERINES
Is he a spy? He's not, is he?
I heard he was born and raised in Busan.
Hey, Kim.
The kid doesn't decide what he is.
That's for Namsan CIA to decide.
You finished the food. Were you hungry?
Keep your head down.
Head down. Is this a theater?
These kids run away
because the government feeds them.
These punks with their heads full of crap
need to be sent to Namsan.
Putting them behind bars
would be patriotic.
How sweet. They're in love.
Have you lost your mind, kid?
You're in the big city now, Jeju boy.
Why roll up your sleeves?
How dare you act tough
in front of a big-city senior officer!
- You punk!
- Are you a lord?
If you hit us, must we take it?
If you send us to Namsan, must we go?
How sweet. Double trouble.
Can you believe this?
These little punks are shameless!
So what if I am?
Is it illegal? Will I get locked up?
Am I going to Namsan?
You smoke, don't you?
You smoke, and you wear miniskirts?
Am I going to Namsan for that?
That lady reported us as runaways, right?
She couldn't say anything else
because she felt guilty.
What else? Did you steal something?
You caused more trouble, right?
We're not being held here
because we hit anyone or stole anything.
We're minors who need the protection
of the Busan Police.
That's why
we're also quietly waiting
for our guardians, so--
- Shall we serve you?
- Don't hit him in the head!
Send this girl to the National Assembly.
Oh man.
I didn't know Romeo and Juliet
were from Jeju.
Aren't you calling your mothers?
They don't need to.
The woman camping out front
is the boy's mother.
What?
This one is handsome.
This one is vixen-like.
Here she comes.
Mom.
- Where's the bag? Where's my stuff?
- What?
Where's my jewelry?
My gold… Good grief!
Where's my gold frog?
Is it real?
It is real gold, isn't it?
It is.
He always does too much.
He's like this
for every wedding anniversary.
He just can't wait to buy me gifts
on special days.
Is that so?
Our cabinet is chock-full of jewelry.
I'm clearing out anything out of style.
Give me a good price.
Is that so?
You gave me a good price
for the jewelry last time.
You came last summer
and said it was your anniversary.
Isn't your anniversary in the summer?
Your husband got you a gold bracelet
back then, right?
No, it's in the spring.
Is that so?
What if it is?
Is that a problem?
Hello.
- How much is it?
- 300 won.
- Give it to me.
- Okay.
- No, give it to me.
- To me.
Give it to me.
Just give it to me.
No, don't give it to her.
Hey, I'm the owner. Why would he pay you?
- Is this your inn?
- It's my money anyway.
This woman stole my bag,
so I'm taking whatever I can from her.
No. Give it to me.
I'll come back later.
Wait, hold on!
Where are you going? Wait…
Just go away.
Gonna stay all night?
Hey, you know
why there are no thieves in Jeju?
Why? Are Jeju folks epically generous?
We wear them down.
We keep going until they're sick of it.
It's the thief, not the victim,
who ends up cracking
because we wear them down.
Wow, you lunatic.
For Christ's sake.
You're a lunatic!
An absolute lunatic!
Completely out of your damn mind!
I'm taking what I'm owed, no matter what.
I'll be here day and night
until I get what my gold toad is worth.
What? Did you say gold toad?
Give me my gold toad.
Hey.
So the gold frog is a gold toad now?
You're the thief--
Do you have a frog's brain?
What can you do?
You should give her the gold frog back.
It's too late now.
Give me a gold toad now.
You're one brazen robber, aren't you?
I bet you've got a criminal record.
You do, don't you?
Should we call the cops?
- Should we call the cops?
- Ma'am!
- What the hell?
Why did you go to the jewelry store? Why?
This will be your tenth offense.
Think of your child, will you?
Let's go.
Don't let anyone from Jeju stay
while I'm away.
Take her away.
Get off me!
This is her tenth offense?
Wow, she's got some nerve.
Hey, you better pay for the fan!
Pay for the fan!
Were you performing circus acts in there?
How did you even manage to break it?
Well done! Great job!
Hey, stop pushing me!
My goodness.
Did you buy the tofu already?
No.
I didn't buy it.
The lady bought it for us.
What about your first birthday rings?
You didn't bring them with you?
Didn't you take them too?
Everything we took was in the bag.
Your dad… That worthless mutt.
Dogs are better
than both you and your father.
Ae-sun, let's go home.
You've really done it this time, Ae-sun.
YESTERDAY WAS YOUR SPRING
You've really done it, Ae-sun.
FACULTY OFFICE
She should've done it on her own.
Why drag down
another family's eldest grandson?
I heard he's one
of the top four athletes in Jeju.
Well, she's the poet of class eight.
Poet, my foot.
She wants to be a poet,
but dating is the best she can do?
POEMS OF YU CHI-HWAN
HANDKERCHIEF OF ETERNAL NOSTALGIA
EXPULSION NOTICE
OH AE-SUN
DUE TO AN UNAUTHORIZED RUNAWAY
AND DISRUPTIVE BEHAVIOR
You've completely ruined your life!
People exaggerate everything
on this island.
I can't even show my face
at the wholesale market.
You've brought shame to our family!
And Jong-gu made us proud?
How can you compare him to her?
A man can lose his land or his home
while running a business.
Why do you keep bringing him up?
Did he run a business? He played cards.
So now what?
What will you do now?
You won't go to the factory.
You can't get married.
Will you die a spinster in this house?
What about him? What did that brat say?
Don't you see your grandmother,
who raised you since you were a baby?
Do you only care about yourself?
How can I face our ancestors?
I'm the one marrying her,
not our ancestors.
What will we say to our ancestors?
That our filial son brought home
an orphan wife, a middle school graduate?
Who brings a middle school graduate
into a noble family as a daughter-in-law?
Why is she a middle school graduate?
What did you expect?
That the school would just give her
a diploma after she eloped at night?
Just go beg there!
Go beg there
so you can become their daughter-in-law.
The whole island knows about their affair.
She's lost any chance
of having a proper marriage.
She can't marry Gwan-sik either.
His grandmother almost fainted.
Wow, Oh Ae-sun.
Heck of a relationship you've got there.
Gambling away your whole life
by eloping at night.
I've only been suspended.
Wow, congratulations.
But why was she the only one
who got expelled?
Middle school graduates can't even solder.
Damn it.
Why was only Ae-sun…
Do you really not know?
It might take two to tango,
but the boy gets called a hero
while the girl's love
gets branded shameless.
Did you ruin her life
without knowing better?
It was my idea.
That fool just followed along.
We should be so proud!
Remove him from the family registry!
No one's punishing my kid!
Ae-sun should be punished.
You don't burn the whole house down
over one maggot.
Why punish someone else's kid?
Our son is the one who's crazy about her.
Seriously, I'm going to take that girl,
scold her, and pinch her, then…
Come on!
Did that work last time?
What good did pulling my hair do?
You want me to lose my grandson
under my nose too?!
You don't catch a chicken
by chasing it with a stick.
You lure it with a worm.
You have to wheedle them.
If you chase them, they'll run miles away.
How could they use a spoon
to lock you away? Seriously.
Oh dear.
Goodness me.
Have you had something to eat?
Yes.
I never skip meals.
I see.
Well, that's good to hear.
Gwan-sik hasn't been able to eat a thing.
Is he on a hunger strike?
You know he'd never do that.
His father told me not to feed him
a single grain of rice.
Ae-sun, even though I want to help,
you know I can't go against
his grandmother, don't you?
I married into this tiresome Yang family,
and I'm still paying the price for it.
You know how stubborn the Yangs are.
Remember how Gwan-sik stole fish from us
to give to you every day for ten years?
I gave your family cabbages
from time to time too.
Where do you think he gets it from?
He gets it from his father.
His father is even willing
to sever ties with him for good.
Goodness.
That's how narrow-minded he is.
I was once so crazy about him,
I even eloped with him at night.
But you can't expect
to live on love forever.
Right up until the wedding,
they'll tell you that you're the only one.
But once married, they forget you.
They're just devoted to their mothers.
You wait and see, okay?
You'll end up alone
in our family for sure.
- Well…
- Yeah, what is it?
Can I ask you something?
We're in a tight spot financially,
and it's been pretty unsettling for us.
We can't even offer your family
a silver spoon.
Still, I'd never let her starve.
What about your family?
Do they approve of her?
Can you beat a shaman?
Your shaman grandma said
that Ae-sun was bound
to her widow mother's spirit.
Everyone here worships the Dragon King
rather than God or Buddha.
No one can stand up to a shaman.
Ae-sun will be living with me,
not my grandmother.
I'll keep Ae-sun safe from her.
So what? Are you planning on moving out?
You have a home in your name?
Who do you think you are,
taking care of me?
Do you think I'm spoiled fish
you can get cheap?
You had her sleep in a room
with fermented soybean bricks?
I won't do it.
It makes me feel small and cheap. No way.
But I want to.
Why? You think
I can't get married unless it's to you?
I'm going to marry a richer,
more handsome man,
a son less precious than you!
Go on, then. Get married.
Take anyone you can!
I won't do it. I'll never marry you.
See if I ever marry you. Just watch me!
Hey! Bring some tea here.
- Miss Ko, serve him some tea.
- Yes, ma'am.
Hello, sir.
So you raised two siblings
all on your own?
That experience
is the main reason I approved of you.
I see.
I heard you really wanted
a man from Seoul.
I'm… pretty much from Seoul.
Right after Korea's liberation,
my wealthy family sent me
to study in Seoul.
If I hadn't married and moved down here,
I could've been a man of power.
At the beginning of my first marriage…
Am I getting that tea anytime today?
Don't worry about what I think.
Love isn't a crime, after all.
I heard a few things
about your past through the grapevine.
But today,
I just took the plunge and came out.
I've crossed the Pacific many times,
so handling a small flaw is no big deal.
I'm more of a Seoul type.
I don't care about things like that.
They say remarriages
work out better for both.
It takes one to know one, you know.
It'd be very demanding to marry someone
who'd never been married.
That would give me a headache.
Are you going to drink that thing?
It cost 50 won.
Sure, he's been married before,
but he owns boats.
Not just one.
To go on a boat in Dodong-ri,
you have to use one of his family's.
If you really want,
I heard he'll try to send you to college
within ten years.
If you do well,
he might even think about
publishing your poetry book.
It's only two children, so…
At least it's not three.
I guess I was born to be a maid.
My goodness.
The spring rain is lasting a long time.
Maybe it's my mom crying.
Maybe she's crying
because I'm getting married like this.
Gwang-rye will be turning in her grave!
You've totally ruined a young girl's life,
and you still have an appetite?
If you're so sad about her,
give her your son.
How does that sound?
No way is she marrying
a man who's been married!
Both families are so determined
to get rid of Ae-sun.
Mak-cheon.
You may perform rituals,
but you have no right
to scold other families.
If she marries that man,
I won't believe in your Dragon King
or the spirits.
Being good should pay off.
Being good should pay!
Stop talking already!
Is Ae-sun getting married?
MADAM BAEK GI-NAM'S 60TH BIRTHDAY
Are you regifting that gift set
to my family?
This is American.
Only it's made in Korea.
It's all the same once you eat it.
I despise all these pointless formalities.
The whole wedding business
is just another meaningless formality.
It's just a way of robbing people.
Honestly, white dresses
are for first weddings.
Let's just wear formal clothes
and take some photos.
Technically, it's not the first
for either of us anyway.
Speaking of which,
I was personally curious about something.
Well…
About Busan.
Does your mother know about this?
Good heavens.
You must've cleared out your entire store.
- Goodness.
- This is as good as theft.
I won't let Ae-sun starve either.
I can give her a whole mackerel every day.
We are no longer living in a time of war.
People don't marry for food.
Are you really her grandmother?
Are you really her uncle?
I knew something was up
when you wouldn't give her any croakers!
Why are you bringing up croakers?
I heard he has already been married.
That he's 30!
Why would you match Ae-sun
with a man like him?
Even the actor Shin Seong-il
wouldn't be good enough for her!
Why would a movie star want Ae-sun?
Why would you throw away
a girl as pretty as Ae-sun?
She's smart, well-spoken,
and really cute.
Why would you? Why?
Keep on yapping.
Let me take her.
I've been giving her croakers for years
and selling her cabbages all this time.
I care about Ae-sun more than anyone else!
More than you!
So why are you taking her from me?
What do you want me to do?
Should I put her on a leash?
Should I put her on a leash
and drag her to marry you?
She doesn't want to.
Who will change her mind?
When a tame cow decides to rebel,
it won't budge.
You can't force it to plow the field.
What's wrong with her?
Go ask your mother.
Ask her how she convinced Ae-sun.
You know, in Busan,
were you caught the day you ran away
or some time later?
I guess kids today will do what they want,
even if they don't stay the night.
How about you, Captain?
Did you separate from your wife
early in the marriage or some time later?
Goddamn it!
You've got a temper.
Yes, I do.
That's why I dislike rude people.
Does that boy know this side of you?
And he still likes you?
- It's why he likes me!
- Goddamn it!
You little punk!
Don't get in the way of this marriage!
Darn it.
It's a party now.
Hey, kid. You little punk!
What? What now?
Let's go.
Come on. Let's go!
Where? Go where?
Got anywhere to go?
Goddamn it! Hey, you!
How dare you be disrespectful
when a grown-up--
Shut it, mister!
Don't go. Marry me.
You have the ring on, so that's it.
What's it for? Can we live off it forever?
Are we running away again?
To become thieves?
Are you really marrying him?
Why would you? Why?
Yeah, he's remarrying and has two kids.
But why would you? Why?
Exactly! Why me? Why only me?
Why do I get all the blame?
Why was I the only one expelled?
Why am I the "shameless" one?
It's over. All of it.
College? Being a poet?
It's all gone to crap.
I can't even become a solderer now.
I said I'd take care of you.
- I've told you a million--
- But how?
What have you done for me since I was ten?
Give me mackerels? Croakers?
I'm not a beggar!
You were ten, but so was I.
- What can a ten-year-old do?
- He said he'd do everything for me.
He'll send me to college
and let me be a poet.
I can do that too!
I'll work on boats.
I'll lay bricks. Anything!
No! I don't want you!
Being with you would be like
always getting a losing roll.
- What?
- I'm tired of having to be so willful.
I'm sick of living with a family
that doesn't want me.
I want to be rich too.
I want to live a comfortable life.
If I marry you,
I'll just get even more mistreated.
But if I marry him,
no one will speak badly of me.
Not even you.
Because you know everything.
You've seen it all. I've…
I've…
lived in shame my whole life.
One of them is free.
Did your mom say so?
Did she say that?
There are six people in the family,
but you only ever buy five.
Do you make a fortune selling fish?
Nosy little brat.
That little punk.
You've seen it all.
I…
I miss her so much.
He told me to go to Busan.
He told me to work at a factory!
I don't have a home anymore.
You know everything,
and you want me to keep living like this?
If I'm with you…
I won't find happiness in marriage.
Please let me live my life.
Let me change the fate you pity so.
Am I
standing in your way?
Gwan-sik.
You have to leave so I can live my life.
You have to leave…
so I can live my life.
For ages, she gazed
at her 18-year-old first love,
whom she would never see again…
and buried her pure love
in that yellow spring.
Tearfully so.
My ring.
They say working in a field is rewarding,
but parenting never is.
Of course you treat me differently.
You'd never treat me like your own child.
Every time she split a fried egg,
my portion was always smaller than yours.
There you go again.
Mom, why did you marry
into a family like this?
I chose my own path.
I only have myself to blame.
I wouldn't choose to live like you.
No way. Never.
I will marry a man from Seoul,
no matter what.
Not a guy who doesn't even know
what "nostalgia" is.
Never!
That's right. You should "never."
So do you regret it? Even a little?
Of course not.
If I hadn't met your father,
none of you would be here.
No, not as a mom.
As Oh Ae-sun.
Just eat your chicken.
What? Tell us.
Do you, Oh Ae-sun, regret it?
Do you think about what could've been?
Oh Ae-sun?
Oh Ae-sun…
was truly broken that spring.
Come on, kids.
They'll die if you touch them. Okay?
Bring us some good ones!
Don't dump leftovers on this island.
If you touch them and they die,
I can't sell them.
Gwang-rye, stop crying.
You should hurry
and send your precious son to safety.
I hope he finds a wife of noble birth
to bring home.
So you actually fed the chicken a worm.
Wow, you're so good. Really.
Scarily good.
Well,
can I ask you something?
Come on, just think of me as your mother.
Well, was Gwan-sik
really one of the top four in Jeju?
Was he close to winning medals?
He probably would've won one by now
if he hadn't been sidetracked.
He wasn't just any fourth.
He was practically third.
Almost tied for third.
That foolish idiot.
Do you guys curse
when you talk to each other?
He said he just went
for the free milk and bread.
He never told me he was good.
How can he follow me around for ten years
and never tell me what he likes?
He always let me go on and on
about becoming a poet, but he…
But he…
That's what guys
in the Yang family are like.
They think they're not supposed
to express their opinions.
Ae-sun.
Gwan-sik…
will lose it all if he's with you.
He will lose his dreams and his family.
You know what being alone is like,
don't you?
Don't take everything away from Gwan-sik.
You have to let him live his life
to the fullest.
Ae-sun.
Let him live his life.
Please.
Am I…
standing in his way?
Am I
standing in your way?
Gwan-sik!
Here!
You're going to make it.
I've coached for ten years,
but you're the only one
who actually ran 100 laps
just because you were told to.
Your mom sells fish
to support your studies on the mainland.
So let's train hard and win a gold medal.
Once you win a gold medal,
you'll forget what she even looks like.
- You know those gold medals?
- Yeah?
They aren't pure gold.
What?
Why work so hard for something
that's not real gold?
I don't need one anymore.
Is your life over or what?
You were the one harping on
about the gold medal and the mainland.
Well, that's because
Ae-sun wished to leave the island.
Does Ae-sun take up most of your life?
My whole damn life.
Get off.
I only ran 100 laps because of Ae-sun.
Selling fish doesn't pay enough,
and my grades aren't great.
I ran 100 laps in the hope
it'd give me a chance.
What lunatic would run that?
Get off, you punk.
The truth is, I actually hate athletics.
What?
It's not for me.
I can't place better than fourth.
Even if they gave me a box of gold…
I would only do it for Ae-sun.
You crazy bastard.
Then why are you going to Seoul right now?
You have to leave so I can live my life.
I'm a pretty modern guy.
I'm open-minded, so I can overlook it.
No other family
would have shown you mercy.
How dare that nobody
speak to me like that!
Goddamn it.
His family runs a fish store
that's about the size of a booger?
He doesn't even own anything,
the impudent little punk.
It's bigger than a booger.
- What?
- It's definitely bigger than your boogers.
Goddamn it. You think
you can disrespect a grown-up
just because I've been nice to you?
Why is a grown-up marrying a child, then?
Goddamn it. Hey, you little brat!
Don't speak to me rudely.
Listen, wake up.
I don't think you grasp the situation.
I might be paying your tuition.
Don't tell me how to speak.
Am I marrying a perfect girl
from a wealthy family?
I don't want your money.
I don't want it.
Really?
Wait, are you serious, miss?
What about college?
What about becoming a poet?
What about the mainland?
I should only rely on my family.
Aren't you marrying me to go to college?
Why else would you?
Why else would you marry me?
I don't have…
anywhere to go.
What?
There's nothing else I can do.
I'm going to do it all.
I'm going to do all of it.
I'll be the chief of the fishing co-op.
I'm also going to be
the president five times.
All right, go on. Do it!
Let's make a king
out of one of our haenyeo crew.
I wonder why she wasn't born as a boy.
How is it that such a little girl
has been gifted with so much potential?
If she has such great potential,
she should run for president.
Go ahead.
You already have eight votes from us.
Nine votes.
That's right! Nine.
What score did you get in math?
What do you want to become?
Don't even ask him!
The First Lady.
- My goodness, kid.
- Look who's got a crush!
I'm getting married
because I have nowhere else to go.
Even if I died, I'd have nowhere to go.
They say living on a pile of dog crap
is better than dying, so…
I'm a pile of dog crap?
Can you just hire me?
I'll be a maid or a babysitter
and make it worth your while.
Hey, listen.
All the housework will be free
if I get a wife, so why would I?
Why would I do that?
As the queen of love,
you may have dreamed of a passionate love,
but I'm just looking for a spouse.
I want a docile daughter-in-law for my mom
and a frugal mother for my children.
For God's sake!
I only met my ex-wife five times
before we got married.
People live like that.
You just have to make a fuss over it,
don't you?
Hey, wait!
Just use the cheapest fabrics here.
Anyway, tell me this.
You spent the night with him?
That crazy little brat!
If she hadn't run that day…
If she hadn't run…
Gyeong-ok, let's go home.
This damn rain. It's bucketing down!
Let's just say it was a rough patch.
Out of sight, out of mind.
Out of mind?
Then why do the Cowherd and Weaver Girl's
tears still rain down on us today?
Gwan-sik!
Where are you going?
How can you just leave me here?
That's right.
Gwan-sik!
How can a young heart resist love?
Yang Gwan-sik!
Hey, Yang Gwan-sik!
Wow, that is loud.
Ae-sun!
Ae-sun! You're going to fall over.
Come here. Aren't you adorable?
Mommy, I want a candy.
Yang Gwan-sik!
Yang Gwan-sik.
Don't go!
Please don't go.
That damn girl is a real pain.
Stop being so obnoxious!
Why don't you stop being so nosy?
Let her be.
Let her yell and scream.
Why do you take everything from me?
Why do you only take everything
that belongs to me?
Mom.
Mom!
Man, what's going on?
Is the Dragon King holding us back?
Why is the wind against us?
Damn it. Hey!
The wind is against us.
Turn this boat around.
- Turn it around!
- We're at sea!
Please turn it around!
Please turn back!
You have to turn around!
Get out of here!
Please turn around for just a second!
Get off me!
Wait! Please!
Why is that little punk on my boat again?
The boat, sir!
Excuse me, Captain!
You have to turn around.
Gwan-sik!
You won't die without her, will you?
Will you die? You fool!
If she hadn't run that day…
If she hadn't run…
You're shattering their lives.
Don't you know
what happened to Romeo and Juliet?
A broken heart doesn't take a life.
Once the boat sets sail,
they're in the hands of the Dragon King.
What's the point of her draining herself?
Let's go.
Ae-sun, let's go.
I'll cook you a pork dish.
Pork is better than a boy?
My goodness.
Oh my goodness.
If she hadn't run that day…
Did someone just fall overboard?
Did someone just…
Mommy, brother go splash.
What?
Brother just go splash.
"A broken heart doesn't take a life"?
It just drove a young man
to jump overboard!
Oh no, Mother.
If she hadn't run that day…
Look! Is that a whale or what?
Something is rushing this way!
If she hadn't run that day,
could she have stopped the destiny
that was rushing toward her?
U-turn!
All the way, Gwan-sik!
Of all the sports,
you just had to teach him to swim!
We should send him
to North Korea as an agent!
Destiny has always been sassy,
just like that.
Goodness me!
Are you okay?
I have to pay for these clothes!
I have money.
- What did that man say?
- I don't know.
All he does is gobble up sugar cubes.
Goodness gracious.
This is better
than the Cowherd and the Weaver Girl.
You know, the thing is,
even the heavens couldn't separate
the Cowherd and the Weaver Girl.
Because they had to let the couple meet
on the seventh day of the seventh month.
Your husband couldn't do it either.
No one can stop young love.
Did you know?
Your parents eloped at night.
Eloped at night?
Your auntie is drunk again.
They caused a total ruckus.
All the seas between Jeju and Busan
were stirred up.
Gyeong-ok,
you're confused again from drinking.
Your mother eloped at night, not me.
But the funny part
is what happened in Busan.
Go home now.
Time to get up.
- What happened in Busan?
- They were caught in two days.
- Enough!
- So how…
All right, drink some water and sober up.
Hey, can you call Gyeong-ok's husband?
Busan worked wonders, I tell you.
- You're a true blessing.
- Gyeong-ok!
Do I have to call your husband over?
Come on!
You arrived earlier than expected.
You were born eight months
after the wedding,
even though they were caught in two days.
That's why Busan worked wonders.
You're such a blessing.
That's why your hometown
is Busan, not Jeju.
Blame it on spring.
Spring has a way of getting to people.
Spring in Jeju
has always arrived early
and has been exceptionally sassy.
I think
we should have maybe three kids.
I think three would be perfect.
So, if we're going to pay
for the education of all three,
we have to be very strategic
about how we live.
Have you heard of General MacArthur?
So, strategically,
we should have a daughter first,
then a son--
No time to waste, then.
What?
No time.
Were you throwing a wild circus in there?
How did you even manage
to break the fan on the wall?
Even my mom thinks
Yang Gwan-sik and Oh Ae-sun broke the fan.
Hey, go home. You little brat.
Go now!
I wondered why they called you "Dia"
before you were born.
It turns out they drank Dia soju
in Busan before they--
If you're drunk, just go, you brat.
You're the ones who went to Busan.
Why take it out on me?
You're the one
who came into my home and ate chicken.
Go home now!
There's some left. Don't tell me to go!
We'll pack it for you to go. Okay?
Put your jacket on. Come on.
Go.
Geum-myeong. Look over here.
One, two, three!
I didn't know a person's head
could be so round.
Are you happy?
I didn't know you could smile like that.
Oh my goodness.
Is she that adorable?
She is. An adorable rascal.
A rascal that held her mother back.
Don't be silly.
Who cares about college now?
I have the whole world right here
in my arms.
You're my nostalgia now, aren't you? Huh?
At the National Sports Festival,
a swimmer who wore boxers
instead of swimming trunks
won first place
in the 400 m and 1,500 m freestyle.
Jo O-ryeon, who burst onto the scene,
expressed his ambitious desire to win
the gold medal at the Bangkok Asian Games.
Are you sad
you couldn't be like Jo O-ryeon?
Who cares about a gold medal
when I've got my golden girl?
She is my dream now.
The spring of their lives
flew by in a heartbeat.
FLAG
THIS IS A SILENT OUTCRY
At the age of 18,
my mom, who had lost her own mom,
became a mother.
At the age of 19,
my dad got his golden girl
instead of a gold medal.
Think she'll be a soccer player?
Look at her legs.
I hope she'll be a teacher.
A literature teacher.
- I wonder what she'll be.
- I know, right?
Their spring wasn't a season
to foster dreams
but to break them.
And they did so willingly.
GEUM-MYEONG, OUR ETERNAL NOSTALGIA
MAY 4, 1969
WHEN LIFE GIVES YOU TANGERINES
Hello, is it okay
if I ask you a few questions?
So you're here to see the flowers today.
How do you feel about them?
The flowers remind me of my first love.
- First love. Of course.
- Go live with her, then.
Hye-ran. That's dirty.
Well, thank you for the interview.
- Hye-ran. It's dirty.
- Okay, then.
Let's interview a few other citizens.
Hello. You must be newlyweds.
These aren't my grandmother's.
They're really mine.
Your first birthday ring
is your mom's, not yours.
But I really want to give her a ring.
You're so tiresome.
Don't look at me like that.
I actually snuck out.
By dawn tomorrow, could--
So you want me to come to work
at dawn because of you?
Fine, leave them here.
Who would live with a man without a ring?
Is the restroom clean?
Clean?
Yeah.
It's usable.
A new ring and a new dress.
This must be a top celebrity's wedding.
Do you really want it?
Is this a wedding or a fashion show?
You should just rent formal wear.
Seriously.
Wear it.
Wear anything you want.
Why not wear your top hat
and strut in a parade?
Pick whatever you want.
For crying out loud.
You like it?
Yeah.
Do you guys want to move out?
If you have the money, just go.
Should I put my hair up?
Does my hair look better up or down?
What?
My hair.
Does it look prettier up or down?
Actually…
Yeah?
Don't you think
you might regret it
in the future?
Why?
I just think it might be…
embarrassing, and…
Do you even know anything about fashion?
Do you know who André Kim is?
No, I don't.
If you have the means, please move out!
This is so annoying.
By the way,
can we have quail noodle soup after this?
You had it just yesterday,
you little piggy.
You look beautiful.
Mom, why did you wear a hat like that?
Was it some kind of dare?
"THE SAME SKY, THE SAME STARS,
ETCHED IN THE SAME HEARTS."
Subtitle translation by: Sung In Jang