WHEN LIFE GIVES YOU TANGERINES
Ae-sun, that brat!
- You brat!
- Mother!
- I don't want him!
- Mother.
Yang Gwan-sik? No, thank you!
No, thank you!
Damn her! Ae-sun, that brat!
Grandma, why are you doing this?
- Why?
- What?
Why did you ruin her cabbages
in the first place?
Why, you little!
She said, "No, thank you."
Barnacles and whelks.
A fishmonger's son
and a haenyeo's daughter.
Same difference.
Am I a maid dating a prince?
Just hanging out doesn't mean
we'll fall for each other.
It's all part of business, you know,
so I could set up shop next to your store.
It's not like I'm dying to get married.
I wouldn't take you
even if they hand you over.
You think I'm crazy?
Why marry a guy from the island?
In any case, my roots are in Seoul.
Gyeonggi Noodle.
Your uncle runs Gyeonggi Noodle.
Gyeonggi-do is practically Seoul.
That damn sea swallowed up
my father and mother.
Seeing the waves all around
makes me feel sick.
You think I'd stay here?
I will marry a man from Seoul,
no matter what.
Not some guy from the island.
Especially not a guy
who doesn't even know what "nostalgia" is.
Never!
You're as quiet as a mouse.
Why aren't you saying anything?
I'd rather live
with a dolhareubang rock statue.
Then take your hand out of my pocket
and put it in a guy's from Seoul.
Give away your son if you want.
It seems like you're okay
with giving him to that girl.
- I'd never go against you, Mother.
- Oh, you wouldn't?
You came to this family knocked up.
Don't push them too hard.
It might lead to an accident.
You know what I mean.
I know. That's why I'm acting like this.
If we leave them alone,
they might elope at night like you did.
Your son will also be stolen
right under your nose.
Are you saying I stole your son, Mother?
Rumors on an island this small
bring nothing but trouble for us all.
Why are you pretending
to be so understanding?
He's just a boy.
They'll hang out for a bit and move on.
Let them be.
Once they've had enough, they'll stop.
Why let it get to you?
You know there's nothing you can do.
The men in the Yang family
have been fools for generations.
They can't tell a snake from a rabbit.
And I'm the mean wench, they say.
Leave them alone.
People pity beggars. They don't love them.
Is it mackerel today?
Being pitiful is wonderful.
My life is full of freebies.
If it were out of pity, I'd feed a beggar.
The school always gives me
the leftover powdered milk.
Like I should be grateful.
You think I gave you fish
for ten years out of pity?
Then why did you give me them?
You think I've spent ten years
as your minion out of pity?
So why did you give me them?
It's about time you told me why.
What are you looking at?
Look at me when you talk to me!
You only ever feed me.
You never make a move.
Did your grandma tell you to hand me fish
and keep your mouth shut?
Did she tell you not to talk to me
in case we get involved…
You little punk! You're such a brat.
Do you kiss little punks?
That was my philtrum!
I wouldn't kiss a beggar either.
Honestly,
who says they like someone like that?
I won't live with my grandma.
I want to live with you.
Seriously,
who on earth would kiss the philtrum
and then say things like…
So stop yapping!
I don't know what happened to me.
I can't hear what you're yapping about.
I can just see your yapping mouth.
What should I do?
You're the selfish brat
who puts her hand in my pocket.
- Why are your lips so shiny?
- I put something on!
- Why?
- To be ready.
What?
I've been ready since I was 14!
SASSY FIRST LOVE
The Jeju Canola Flower Festival
has started again this year.
Jeju Island is bustling with tourists
who have gathered
to see the scenery of the canola flowers.
Especially this year,
a variety of events for couples
are capturing attention.
Let's interview some of the visitors here.
Hello. Is it okay
if I ask you a few questions?
So you're here to see the flowers today.
How do you feel about them?
The flowers remind me of my first love.
- First love. Of course.
- Yes.
Go live with her, then.
Hye-ran, that's dirty.
Mom, was Dad your first love?
Was he?
I don't know. I forget.
Your first kiss?
Are you insane?
That's our mom you're talking about!
You must be out of your damn mind.
Yeah, just get lost.
The flower field is so pretty.
- It is.
- Our Jin-hee is prettier than a flower.
Did you know
canola flowers have a very strong scent?
The scent is so strongly sweet.
It gives you such a headache.
You feel like you might faint.
I'm hungry!
Why haven't you eaten yet?
Can't you just get rid of this thing?
Dinner will be ready in no time.
Why would you watch something so boring?
MARINATED CHICKEN
Back then,
if I'd known that spring was truly spring,
I would've lived my life to the fullest.
I still won't marry you.
It's just that, you know,
today's training was so tough...
Shut up and just walk.
That bald young man
Commuting at eight o'clock
I can't wait to see
If I'll see him again tomorrow
Sun-nam was eating
And now she's gone
And now she's hiding
I found you!
Spring is ever so fickle.
Just as it starts to feel warm,
it turns cold.
Just as it feels cold, it turns hot.
It rushes at you so fast,
leaving you dazed.
What did we do wrong?
Min-ok.
Morally speaking,
I have never been married.
At least my legal marriage record
is clean.
Min-ok.
Why should I have to take care
of your late wife's child?
Are you serving a master?
Why are you trying to save face?
Come next year, you’ll--
Are you serving a master or something?
Mom, Jong-gu is your eldest grandson,
even if he drains everything we've got.
He'll perform your annual ancestral rites
after you're gone.
What is it?
Is something bothering you?
So what if it is?
You've cared for that family,
and now you want something from us?
Grandma, don't you have a room?
Do you all sleep and eat in that room?
If your family is struggling like this,
you should work at a factory
or something to help out.
Why are you taking care of another family?
Do they pay you enough for this?
It's not to make a living.
It's just to buy some snacks.
And now what?
Are you a literary girl?
You want to go to a college
that even Jong-gu didn't attend?
What?
Do you want to go to college?
Mom, do you have savings to give her
when we're in this state?
Get that family to pay you as a maid
so you can go to college!
Even if we had plenty of spoiled rice,
we wouldn't give it
to a dog that ran away.
Why did you take them down?
They're not yours! Why did you do it?
They're not even yours!
You expect me to live with a picture
of his late wife hanging above my head?
Sun-nam, Sun-bong. What were you doing
when she took down the picture?
Are ice pops all that matter?
See this girl playing politics?
She's already acting sly
to win them over to her side!
You shouldn't have only bought
four ice pops.
Why would I buy five?
Do I have to please
your late wife's kid too?
- Min-ok.
- Forget it.
Morally speaking,
you should show some decency.
- Min-ok.
- Yeah, forget it.
Give me my money.
Then I'll leave,
even if you beg me to stay.
Wait.
You borrowed money from a child too?
Min-ok!
Would I ever do that?
I would never--
Give me my money for tuition.
You said if I raised your kids,
you'd send me to college.
I see.
He looked after you
when you had nowhere to go.
Now you want money too?
Give me my money. You promised!
I even sold those cabbages.
Why won't you pay me?
You said you were too scared
of my mom to scam me!
What's scary about a dead wife?
He's scared of his kids
growing up so fast.
Min-ok!
Next year,
he'll have three kids of his own.
Why would he pay your tuition?
More importantly,
Yeom Byeong-cheol is dirt poor.
Rumor has it that he's living with me
because he can't pay me back.
- Na Min-ok.
- What? Damn you, Byeong-cheol!
Don't you get it? He had you fooled.
You're on your own now.
Of course, you're on your own now.
What did you expect?
DECEMBER 1967
Everyone looks out for themselves in life.
Right now, soldering is the best.
They teach you a skill, feed you,
pay you, and make you a patriot.
This is your best bet.
It's also on the mainland,
just like you've always wanted.
Grind for a few years,
finish the apprenticeship,
and they'll pay you 15,000 won a month.
Eat and sleep at the factory,
and you won't have to spend any money.
So send us half the money every month.
Every single month.
The eldest grandson's debt is also yours.
Jong-gu has to do well
for you to find a good husband.
It's better to be born a cow
than to be born a woman in Jeju.
That's what my mom said.
Jong-gu has been holding
ancestral rites for your father.
What would you know?
Jong-gu's rice is getting cold.
I'm not working at the factory.
I won't go.
I won't clean up after my siblings
or the eldest grandson.
No one.
If you don't work, where will you go?
You want to live in this tiny house
just to add to our troubles?
I won't. I won't do any of it.
If I keep living this way like a fool…
it'll make my mom cry.
Ae-sun,
think about it.
Your mom is gone.
Right?
There isn't a warm spot waiting
to welcome you in the world.
How many rooms do you have?
Can you win against your grandmother?
You'd lose, wouldn't you?
What happened? Who upset you this time?
He told me to go to Busan.
He told me to work at a factory!
I don't have a home anymore.
Sun-nam and Sun-bong
got won over with ice pops.
My grandma's family is broke.
There isn't a warm spot in the world
that will welcome me.
The only person in the world
who cares about me at all
is you, Yang Gwan-sik.
So…
Why should I?
Why do I have to end up
with a guy from the island?
This is a silent outcry
A handkerchief of eternal nostalgia
Waving toward the blue sea
I will marry a man from Seoul,
no matter what.
A pure heart flaps like…
A pure heart flaps in the wind like waves
Especially not a guy
who doesn't even know what "nostalgia" is.
Never!
The first man to hang…
Oh, who could it be
The first man to hang
A sad and sorrowful heart in the air
So what if you know what "nostalgia" is?
What about college?
What about becoming a poet?
What about the mainland?
I can't give you everything.
But there's one thing I will do for you,
no matter what.
Come on.
Can't you at least just say
you'll give me everything?
Just tell me you will give me
the moon and the stars!
How can I live with someone like this?
I don't know. I can't lie.
You'd actually lose to your grandmother,
wouldn't you?
This is a silent outcry
Shut up.
Stop it already!
A handkerchief of eternal nostalgia…
FEBRUARY 1968
You don't have to fight to win.
Even if you're the pro wrestler
"The Headbutt" Kim Il,
it's better to avoid than to fight.
I might be running away,
but I must take what I'm owed.
Your grandma might want
to put me behind bars.
You won't regret this?
Once we leave Jeju by boat,
there's no backing down.
Don't!
There are no take backs in life.
If your life and my life
join together as one,
we stick it out together
whether we live or die.
So if you're scared, walk away now.
Just go back home!
In all the 19 years of my life…
I've never felt more excited.
- How fast can you run 100 meters?
- Twenty-four seconds?
Forget it. Let's go.
Who can stop the spring that barges in?
FEMALE RUNAWAY PREVENTION PERIOD
Spring in Jeju
always seems to come
particularly early.
To honor the bloodless May 16 Coup,
known as the Revolution of Spring,
events are being organized
across the entire country.
For this…
That spring,
their coup d'état was as ambitious
as their first voyage…
Even as the nation faced the threat
North Korean Kim Shin-jo's team posed,
the president decided to…
…but it wasn't as revolutionary
as they'd hoped.
Provincial ID.
Without any ID,
we'll assume you're with Kim Shin-jo.
You said you were grown-ups.
Let's see your IDs.
Why are you sitting in the corner,
looking scared?
What are you saying?
I don't get it.
Excuse me…
You're minors, right?
Sir?
You kids are runaways.
How did you end up with her?
What are you saying?
I have no idea what you mean.
Kids today are so shameless.
How dare you board this ship
by yourselves?
- Then just throw us overboard.
- What?
Throw us overboard here.
What's with the attitude?
Do you come from a wealthy family?
Is your father a politician?
Throw us off.
What? Who are you?
What?
What are you?
Husband and wife.
What?
We're husband and wife.
We're adults, so we got married.
How can kids get married?
Let's go, honey.
What are you?
Husband and wife.
What am I meant to do with these?
Why are you being so rude to us?
Are these even yours?
Are Busan people always rude to customers?
We're all adults here.
Did you steal these?
They are his grandmother's.
I need to see some IDs.
We left them behind.
Yeah, right.
I'm sure you left them behind.
I was born in early 1949.
Year of the Tiger?
- Exactly.
- It's actually the Year of the Ox!
What are these? Did you steal them?
- Are you thieves?
- We're runaways.
NAMPOJANG INN
We have neither a provincial ID
nor a citizen ID.
Our wallets were stolen,
so we don't have anything.
Take it out.
Maybe we can get a room with this first.
Probably not, right?
Sort of like a pawn shop?
Newlyweds?
You look like newlyweds.
Are you on your honeymoon?
That's fine.
You can pay us tomorrow.
How generous of you!
Are we running a charity?
Your wallets were stolen
on your honeymoon.
You must be really upset.
You'll give us a room?
Don't let being robbed upset you.
Busan folks are epically generous.
You could try standing up to her.
Is your grandmother that scary?
I'm not scared of her.
Does standing up to her
make you a bad child,
but running away isn't as bad?
I'm not scared of my grandma.
Yeah, right.
I'm scared she'd give you grief.
Are you okay
with giving up on athletics?
I'm not even that good.
I did it for the free milk and bread.
What are you, a pig?
You take the GED test.
I'll work at the factory.
Do you know
why I'm marrying Yang Gwan-sik,
the lamest boy in all of Jeju?
Steel.
You're like steel.
We may have hungry days,
but you'll never break my heart.
Even if someone gave me
a gold or silver axe,
the steel axe is mine.
The steel axe is the real deal.
Nobody would give you
a gold or silver axe anyway.
The lamest guy for sure.
You said we were married.
Doesn't seem like it.
This doesn't seem like it at all.
Yang Gwan-sik.
Excuse me.
Why so happy? She stole all your rings.
She took your yellow dress too.
You know, the woman at Gwan-sik's house,
her gold frog was taken.
She had both her gold frog
and her son taken.
Is that why you're happy?
Do you find it amusing?
The boy's grandmother almost fainted.
Man, they're so bold.
How did they even think
of running away to Busan?
Rumor has it that they caused
quite a scene on that ship.
They're saying
Ae-sun led the whole ruckus.
Ae-sun is a bit of a romantic, isn't she?
They're lovers on the run, so to speak.
Does romance pay the bills?
Once they get hungry,
they'll start resenting each other.
So what if they're hungry?
You know, at their age,
they'd be happy to just spend all day
eating tangerines together
on a heated floor.
Min-ok.
Were you happy?
I don't remember
having tangerines with you.
Let's do it now.
Hey, you there?
Write down what she was wearing.
I heard she stole your clothes.
Are you going after them?
You're like a bounty hunter.
It's a good look for you.
How are you going to find them?
You'll never find them.
- Quit rambling and write it down.
- I don't know what she was wearing.
What?
I'm a door-to-door saleswoman.
I have tons of clothes.
It's their first night.
Shut your trap!
Epically generous, right?
This is the crown jewel of Busan.
It'd be a shame if you didn't try it.
Is this really all on the house?
Well, Busan is a big city.
The floor's all warm now.
Enjoy a few glasses of this soju
and have a nice rest.
If you lie on this heated floor
while tipsy,
you'll melt like butter in a frying pan.
But don't just melt right away.
Take your time.
Get busy, if you catch my drift.
It is your first night, isn't it?
Look at you!
You're both blushing. Get right to it.
You've come to the right place.
Even the most inexperienced men
leave this place as experts.
Ma'am!
Oh my.
Mind yourself.
Give it your all.
Give it your all!
Jaecheop-guk for sale.
Yes, over here, please. It's really good.
Is the bathroom clean?
Clean?
Yeah.
It's usable.
Wait.
Did you do that?
I think the screw just came loose.
Just leave it, then.
What if they ask us to pay for it?
Busan folks are epically generous.
BILL
TOTAL: 640 WON
Didn't she say
everything was on the house?
What?
What's this?
What is this?
That hurt.
What?
What's wrong?
What? What is it?
- Our bags.
- What?
- Where are our bags?
- Bags?
No one else got robbed?
Were there any strange guests?
What are you trying to pull?
Sorry?
Quit joking around and pay up.
Additional charges for room service
and for breaking the fan mount.
The broken mount is the evidence.
- Why would it be broken?
- Yeah!
The thief entered in the dark and--
We know! You broke the mount.
We're certain it was you.
Why us?
One of the guests
might have seen something.
- You could ask.
- Yeah.
So they know
people get robbed in this inn?
Well, maybe your wife saw something.
- Yeah.
- Sorry?
I never saw any bags at all.
You came here empty-handed.
On the house.
- Hey.
- Yes?
Did you see these guys with any bags?
Wait, what?
This came from one of the bags.
Only this was left on the floor.
You had no bags, so we took pity on you.
Now you want us to give you one?
I mean, yesterday, we took our key
after setting down our bag here.
You must be really upset.
Why don't we just call the police?
Should we call
and tell them these kids are runaways?
Busan folks are epically generous.
This is the crown jewel of Busan.
It'd be a shame if you didn't try it.
SPY AWARENESS PROMOTION PERIOD
BUSAN POLICE
MISSING PERSONS
YANG GWAN-SIK, MALE, AGE 19
HANDSOME
OH AE-SUN, FEMALE, AGE 18
VIXEN-LIKE
Yes.
Ma'am, you may as well
look for a needle in a haystack.
How will you find kids
who were determined to run away?
I'm running out of coins, Mother.
Stop telling me about your dreams.
I have to go, okay? Bye.
A conception dream?
Why would the rooster kidnap the kids?
Are you telling me
you want to eat chicken right now?
Cock-a-doodle-doo.
Newlyweds?
Here's the chicken you ordered.
Enjoy!
Do you think I'm an idiot?
Did you think you had me fooled?
Why did you give us a room and alcohol
if we had no bags or money?
Quit yapping.
Let's call the police now.
They'll call your mother in Jeju
and tell her to come here.
I need to teach this girl a lesson.
How did you know we were from Jeju?
Go. Yeah, just leave.
- I'll just think of it as bad luck.
- Hold on!
How did you know that we're from Jeju?
Should we call the police
and go over the details one by one?
The boat tickets.
You found them
in the bags you stole, right?
You birdbrain.
My suitcase.
Our bags!
Give them back to us!
They're all we have left.
My mom's picture is in that suitcase.
My suitcase.
You kept the room warm,
kept pouring us drinks,
and made us "melt like butter"
just to steal our bags!
They stole all those towels too.
SUBONGYONG SAUNA
NAMPO BARBERSHOP - JUNGANG SAUNA
You thief!
Thieving… bitch.
Got any proof?
You saw our boat tickets.
So what if we did?
Got any proof?
Scram while we're still being nice.
Or we'll sell you both to God knows where.
Those bags were all we had.
That was the only picture I had of my mom.
The gold frog was in there too.
It's not like we're beggars or anything.
We're like those kids in the fairy tale
who were lured by breadcrumbs
and captured by a witch.
I don't know what that is.
Hansel and Gretel.
Never heard of it.
I always thought
they were the biggest idiots.
They lost their minds over the food
and had no idea
they were about to be devoured.
What happened to those kids?
Did they survive?
Killed.
The witch killed them?
No.
They killed her.
The children threw…
the witch into an oven
and burned her alive.
Ae-sun.
They killed her,
took all her silver, gold, and treasures,
and lived happily ever after.
Oh Ae-sun.
Those kids were really something.
It's all on the house.
Busan folks are epically generous.
Have a drink in this warm room,
and you'll melt like butter
in a frying pan.
This right here is--
What happened to that?
Damn it!
Yesterday, some lunatics came in here
and caused a total ruckus!
- Let me climb on your back.
- Okay.
Hurry.
Those little punks came in here
and made us flip out.
I wanted to throttle them,
but I let them go.
We're decent folks, you know?
What is it now?
Excuse me.
I don't need any more free stuff.
That free stuff--
If you get drunk, they'll rob you.
She said you'll melt like butter, right?
What are you saying?
Don't turn the lights off, no matter what.
Why isn't that girl sleeping?
Well, we're not making any money tonight.
Charge her double for the soju.
The gold frog and my mom's picture
come first, got it?
We look for our stuff first.
If we can't find it,
we take their cashbox, okay?
We'd still be in the red.
That gold frog is worth way more.
It's not like we're stealing.
It was all we had for our future, right?
Gwan-sik.
You're the head of our family now, okay?
Honey.
Let's go.
It's not there.
Not there.
Don't do it. Get the cashbox.
The cashbox.
Let's just go.
Let's go. I'll buy you another one.
Hey!
- The cashbox.
- Hey, lady!
Put it down.
- Right, 24 seconds.
- Put the cashbox down.
- Damn it, you punk.
- Put the cashbox down!
I swear I'll beat this girl to a pulp!
I'm done for. Just go!
Go!
Just go!
You want us to sell this girl to a place
where no one can find her?
Lady, that's the pit of my stomach.
My stomach.
Put it down before I lose it.
- Come at me.
- Put it down!
Come at me.
Okay, let up a bit.
- I'm dying!
- Hey, be quiet.
Put it down. Now!
- Lady.
- Look at that punk.
That's right. Just go.
- Put it down!
- Run along just like that, punk.
Off you go, punk.
Go!
Seriously!
I told you to put it down, punk!
That's right. There you go.
What the hell is he doing?
Mom's first love
was the karate master Choi Bae-dal.
As for Mom,
she was the pro wrestler Kim Il.
"THE SAME SKY, THE SAME STARS,
ETCHED IN THE SAME HEARTS"
Subtitle translation by: Sung In Jang