WHEN LIFE GIVES YOU TANGERINES
Careful.
One, two.
Be careful.
Even if a million miles lie ahead of you…
Please, mister!
That's really upsetting me! Be gentle!
…your greatest worry
is the one in front of you.
- Can you lift this?
- One, two.
Look, do we really have to take this up?
Even if we do, there's nowhere to put it.
You wanna sleep with this huge thing
in that tiny place?
This is my wedding furniture.
My very first.
If you're downsizing,
you should take less stuff.
Who cares about a mother-of-pearl wardrobe
these days? All wrapped up…
It's Tongyeong mother-of-pearl.
All right, let's take it up.
- Let's take it up!
- Take it up.
Okay!
- One more person.
- Okay.
Let's tilt it.
Seriously!
So why did we have to move?
- Is that brat your only child?
- "Brat"?
Cheol-yong's sister is a bus conductor.
She gives him pocket money.
Is that brat…
Is she the pillar of our home?
She's why it's falling apart.
- Damn it.
- "Damn it"?
Why are you always so tough on me?
You'd better fix your hair.
Do you go to school to make people laugh?
- Pull it.
- Get ready to pull. Lift it!
Here we go.
What's wrong with this?
Oh no.
What's that?
Is it going to be a shoe cabinet now?
Where are your aunties?
They butted in at my circumcision,
so where are they now?
They are busy because of the Olympics.
I really don't get it.
Why are they involved in the Olympics?
They say haenyeo represent Jeju.
When they were given those roles,
they quickly made up with the government.
What else is there for them to do
but make up?
Where are you going?
You have a test coming up.
You want me to waste money on college too?
Are you gonna move to a hut next?
What about that darn wardrobe?
You said it was your wedding furniture!
What? Am I starving you or something?
Why do you always go on about money?
Stop wasting electricity!
Off to Cheol-yong's again?
Come here.
This is a little better.
A little.
I'll wallpaper the living room, too,
in one of those floral prints you love.
It's already peeling.
You picked the perfect spot
for the wardrobe.
You can hang clothes
as soon as you come home,
so the flow's perfect.
You're the smart one,
so you pick everything perfectly.
Why are you so talkative all of a sudden?
Shall we go with floral curtains?
Let's do it. Call the home decor store.
- Call--
- It's fine.
I like this place.
It's just the wardrobe.
It holds a special place in my heart.
That's why I got annoyed.
Now you're laughing?
Have you ever lived in an apartment?
How will you handle
being cramped up in here?
Where will you hang blankets
or store big sauce jars?
I've never been picky
about where we lived.
Whether it was at your parents' house
or a one-bedroom rental,
wherever you were was home to me.
You should've married a rich man.
Oh Ae-sun loves books
and enjoys being coy.
You were born to be a rich man's wife.
All the wives in Dodong-ri
are jealous of me.
Who else gets to live
in a flower field like this?
Really.
This wallpaper is so outdated.
Where did you even get it?
Even if a million miles lie ahead of you…
Go. You'll get paste on you.
…your greatest joy
is the one in front of you.
You gave your kid everything,
so now you're back to a street stall.
You're just as stubborn as Gwang-rye.
"Sun and the Three Aunties'" was fine.
AUNTIES' SEAFOOD HOUSE
I didn't even pay anything,
so why put my name on it?
I don't like that. I really don't!
After all these years,
does a sense of shame feed you?
For so long, you've been clinging
to something that doesn't even make money.
Charge me for setting up a stall here.
Why wouldn't you charge me?
I want to make it clear
I'm only selling appetizers.
I will never sell what you sell!
Why are you like this again? Why?
How do you have time to play with a ball?
Whatever!
And that hair!
Where did you get the money to do that?
Whatever!
You're selling stuff again, aren't you?
For heaven's sake,
you're driving me up the wall!
- Whatever!
- She's soaking wet.
Turn off the faucet. Hurry.
Ae-sun's clock is smashed.
You'll hurt yourself. Move your hand.
He didn't even eat. Where did he go?
Good grief, he's always going
to Cheol-yong's.
Young children are so easy to treat, huh?
No matter what you do, they still
look for you and call out, "Mom."
Don't walk all over them
'cause they're easy to treat.
A young leaf can be torn
by even a gentle rain.
Auntie, when will I be fully grown?
I'm not yet either.
None of us have fully grown up…
You even bought a big one. Why?
Are you bribing us
to take good care of your wife?
Yes.
His people skills are improving.
…but every time our hearts
felt growing pains,
we all grew a little.
What's going on?
Hey, finish that later and come out here.
Come out!
Where do we stand?
- Auntie!
- There you are.
- To the middle.
Hey, come here.
All right. Are we good?
- Wait.
- What?
- Come on.
- Leave my hair alone.
One, two, say kimchi!
Didn't I tell you to stop setting up
that stall on the street?
I told you I hate
that you eat out on the street every day!
What did she write here?
COME AND CHECK US OUT!
FRESH FISH DAILY, STRAIGHT FROM THE BOAT
MARKET PRICES ALL DAY
There are moments when the heart grows.
Seeing them on the street again
because of me, I made a vow to myself…
never to take their dreams away again.
SONG YEONG-SAM
SAN-108, BONGCHEON 5-DONG
Boarding houses near the school
can be quite expensive.
Though it's hilly here,
it's good for your health.
INTEREST RATE SOARS
JAPAN'S ECONOMY UNSTABLE
But if you could just fix the room door…
He's just a kid. What's the big deal
if a kid comes and goes?
Still, if you could just install
a latch inside…
What, don't you trust us?
You're a funny one, aren't you?
The one who lived here before you
never said a word.
He called him over and looked after him,
saying how cute he was.
Come on, take a look.
Look how adorable he is.
Right.
He is cute.
You know it's harder to find a room
or boarding house
than an apartment these days.
We have the luxury to choose our tenants,
but you don't have much choice.
YEONG-SIM
YEONG-SIM'S DREAM
Perhaps Yeong-sim had many dreams
because her family owned a home in Seoul.
Let's all just be easygoing.
Sure, easygoing.
- It's me who needs to be easygoing.
- That reminds me.
I'm saying this
because you remind me of my daughter.
No boyfriends allowed.
If you bring one, I'll kick you out.
No Park Chung-seop.
If you were my daughter,
I'd break your legs.
If I'm like your daughter, a door latch--
DO NOT ENTER! KNOCK!
Quiet. If they catch you, we're dead.
Hello?
Your son Cheol-yong
is here.
Yes.
It's time for MacGyver to be on now,
but my son is still in his room.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Cheol-yong really is something.
If he was so afraid of his dad yelling,
he shouldn't have come last in his class.
Not only did he come in last,
but now he's run away from home!
Why lock the door?
Privacy.
What was that?
Come on, get out of my room!
This isn't your room.
Did you buy this place?
Whatever!
Is that all you'll ever say to me?
"Whatever"?
Get out!
- You just don't get it.
- What did you say?
Then what do we do?
If you keep your mouth shut,
what should I do?
So let's just call it quits now.
You'd shave if you cared--
It's not that I don't love you.
Show me how I can stop loving you!
So now what?
Can you quit
and get your teaching certificate?
I have my own level too.
I have to marry
better than Suk-gyeong did.
Are your worthless paintings
more important than I am?
Should I stick egg cartons on the wall?
Can you beat my father? At least shave!
Do I mean less than your facial hair?
Dad, give me the biggest one, okay?
Give my sister the smallest one!
Okay.
The key is not there.
Bu-seon, are you here?
- Bu-seon!
Song Bu-seon!
He's going through puberty!
What's so special about it?
Remember when you'd steal those croakers,
mackerels, and tilefish for me?
Your mom said she wished she dropped dead.
Here.
Hey.
I can beat my mom.
I do beat her.
Wait a minute.
Why two forks?
Why did Mom bring two?
Bu-seon!
Song Bu-seon!
I think I chose the wrong place to live.
- What are you doing?
Song Bu-seon!
Song Bu-seon! Open the door!
MILITARY MAIL
FROM PARK YEONG-BEOM
Bu-seon.
- Open the door!
- Open up!
- Not gonna open it?
- What the hell?
- Open this door now!
- Oh my God.
Song Bu-seon!
Who are you?
Open it now!
Are you crazy?
What are you doing right now?
Hey! Open the door now!
Sir, ma'am, could you please
save me this one time?
My dad will kill me for real.
Please, just once.
Just this once.
The fluffy guy had the eyes
of a mole being chased by a hunter.
So I let it happen.
Father, I…
Well, I wanted to share some steamed buns.
I was wondering how you were settling in.
Well,
why are you home so early?
How about the factory?
When were you ever interested
in my factory?
This closet is more spacious
than it looks, isn't it?
Dad, what about dinner--
It's perfect for your blankets, isn't it?
Yes, of course it isn't.
"Of course it isn't"?
Actually, you know,
I really should go now.
You know what?
We provide the tenant with a wardrobe.
She says she has to go.
Wait… That's where my underwear…
Why open a tenant's wardrobe?
I think it's really time
for me to take my leave.
Okay. Yeah, sure.
But why are you standing there?
Well, you know…
I was just wondering if a new tenant came.
You never cared
about what happens at home.
You only care about
having the freedom to date.
Come on. That's not…
Come out.
Come out now.
- Dad, you know…
- Mr. Song.
Landlord, my lord…
Do you want to walk out?
Or should I drag you out?
Come out!
Cheol-yong, come out.
Come on. We said we'd go easy on them.
Park Cheol-yong!
Come out!
Park Chung-seop!
When Grandma Min-ok turned 60, she said,
"Morally speaking,
there is no place to hide in a house
but the wardrobe."
Excuse me.
Could you…
I'm sorry.
So sorry.
It was embarrassing,
but that's how we first met.
You punk. Cheol-yong, you little punk.
Your father lost his nails.
Did you even know that?
He works tirelessly
at the wholesale market.
How dare you run away from home like…
How can you…
get smaller?
He's smaller.
Cheol-yong?
Who are you?
Are you
a girl?
Oh my God.
So what happened
to your hair?
Did you cut it at home?
Is your family struggling?
No.
I was punished.
You know,
on the bag…
By any chance,
does YEM happen to be "Yang Eun-myeong"?
Yes.
Why do you have Eun-myeong's initials
on your backpack?
Are you guys close?
Are you?
We're dating.
My goodness.
- It's been 500 days.
- Where's the duster?
You need to be beaten 500 times!
But you two started dating
in elementary school.
- We're much classier.
- Hey!
Who told you that?
Aunt Gyeong-ok!
Call Yang Gyeong-ok over!
Love isn't misconduct!
What'd you say, you punk?
This is a silent outcry
A handkerchief of eternal nostalgia
Waving toward the blue sea
Oh, who could it be
The first man to hang…
At first, I didn't like her
because of her mustache.
But after ten years of seeing her,
one day, I stopped noticing it.
What was I supposed to do?
I don't want to hear this.
I'm just a supplement here anyway!
But this girl says I'm the best.
She likes me more than her brothers!
Good for you, dummy. Happy?
Yang Eun-myeong was just like Dad,
a sucker for love…
The thing is,
I've always liked naughty boys.
…but not his taste in girls.
But still,
you shouldn't have run away from home.
Do your parents know?
They probably don't know yet.
I left this morning.
Which school do you go to?
What's your name?
Don't you have a name?
Hmm… suk.
Can't Suk speak?
Bu Hyeon-suk.
Hello.
Why is your last name…
Are you a Bu?
Yes.
I can't even.
How can a love scandal
span two generations in such a small town?
It happens because it's a small town.
How did they have kids the same age
in such a small town?
I couldn't come to help
with your move or to make kimchi.
So, in other words,
the two families had their meet-and-greet
when they were both pregnant.
Hyeon-suk, never step on a pile of poop.
You have to marry a man
like this lady's husband, okay?
Hyeon-suk is also about to enter
Dodong Elementary, right?
They went to the same school for ten years
in this small town, so no surprise there.
Did you give your daughter your all
but go hands-off with your son?
Do you know what kind of kids
your son hangs out with?
Statistically, it'd be stranger
if they didn't get involved.
There's this unbelievable girl
in the girls' class.
He would never cause trouble with girls.
Eun-myeong can't get along with them.
He can't even hang out with his sister.
Is it the same with sisters?
I can't hang out with mine either.
But it's more to do with taste
than statistics.
Actually, taste can run in the family too.
Indecency runs in that family!
I named my daughters
Hyeon-suk for "virtuous"
and Jeong-suk for "pure."
And I like those who are virtuous.
Bu Hyeon-suk, get out of there now!
At least come in and say hello.
Are they getting married?
In my opinion,
Sang-gil had a bit of a crush on Ae-sun.
Goddamn it.
AUNTIES' SEAFOOD HOUSE
He did have a crush.
Passion runs in the family.
Everyone in her family
knows nothing but romance.
Are you having fun?
Are you mad?
Are you really that mad right now?
What's the matter?
You've had quite the spring yourself.
There's no stopping spring.
Could you have resisted the spring breeze?
Could you or couldn't you?
My dear has a mouth but nothing to say.
Kwon Gye-ok is having a blast.
It's like she's waited for this
her whole life.
If you're really careful, you'll lose
your son right under your nose too!
Mother, it's your grandson
we're talking about.
My strawberry-like innocence at 18
If my own mom doesn't understand me
What should I do?
Are you all planning to be singers?
Stop watching that folk music show.
President Roh Tae-woo
has declared war on crime and violence.
People find ways to sleep together
while fleeing.
Even in wartime,
flowers bloom, and people fall in love.
Let them be
so they can do their thing.
To address urgent safety issues
like kidnapping and serial murders…
They're now in the spring of their lives.
GHOST
NOVEMBER 24, CANNES THEATER
RACETRACK PART-TIME JOB
SALES ASSISTANT WANTED
EXCHANGE STUDENT IN TOKYO
LOOKING FOR JAPANESE TRANSLATION JOBS
CLASS OF '87, ENGLISH LITERATURE
YANG GEUM-MYEONG
Unlike TV dramas, studying abroad doesn't
throw you a golden lifeline in real life.
KOREAN-JAPANESE TUTOR
Darn it.
Why did these kids post theirs
right next to mine?
Life flowed at a step-by-step pace.
You can put those posters up
whenever you want, right?
Can you put them up anytime
as long as you meet your quota?
Hello again.
Are you
looking for a part-time job?
Yeah, I guess.
But you know,
this is my job.
Anything that involves a brush is my job.
Right, I see.
Go ahead.
GHOST
CANNES THEATER
The premiere of Ghost is tonight
at 7:00 p.m. at the Cannes Theater.
PART-TIME USHER
CANNES THEATER
In Chapter Three, they begin
by mentioning the US, but as you all know…
Come on, seriously.
Why is this woman fully clothed?
Who told you to paint Ong-nyeo dressed?
BYEON KANG-SOE 3
That's what your Picasso said?
People come to the theater
to see Ong-nyeo.
They're not here to see
some greenery you painted.
Go to the Piccadilly
or Danseongsa movie theater.
Who paints Byeon Kang-soe
like a piece of scenery?
Why do you keep trying to make art
with other people's money?
Did you buy these paints?
Did I give you this basement
as your personal gallery?
I depicted the joys and sorrows
of Ong-nyeo and Kang-soe
through these Korean mountains--
What about my joys and sorrows?
I'm the one
with the greatest sorrows here!
A painting isn't a photograph--
Oh, Artist Park!
No, Artist My Lord! Your Artistic Majesty!
Please spare me.
I beg you, please. Please have mercy!
- Here to see a movie?
- I'm not buying.
She's here again.
Lady! Stop scalping!
Reselling our tickets is not allowed!
A basement Picasso.
There's a Picasso
in the basement of the Cannes Theater.
He never talks back,
but he's as stubborn as a bull.
He hangs his head
like he's done something wrong
but keeps painting his own way.
So who can blame the owner?
I'd lose it too.
So he's actually an artist?
I guess you could say that.
Billboard painters
are usually no-name artists.
But he doesn't get fired?
The owner is a softy.
Sorry?
He feels bad for yelling,
so buys some snacks and slinks downstairs.
I see.
So how do you know each other?
Why did he introduce you to us?
I just ran into him somewhere.
Two tickets, please.
But, honey, you run into them
and end up living with them.
Next.
TELL US THE NAME OF THE MOVIE
Just one, please.
Next.
TICKET
GHOST
- Excuse me.
- How many tickets?
I don't want Ghost.
Byeon Kang-soe is on later at night. Next.
Did you see it?
- Next!
- Do you want to see it with me later?
Are you going to buy a ticket?
I guess crazy guys watch movies too.
Seriously?
Ma'am!
Ma'am, can you take over for a bit?
Yeah.
SHOWTIMES
GHOST
It's Christmas, you know!
So I'm here.
Look at you in those overalls!
You look thinner.
You're still cute.
Should I shoot them with the projector?
How do you know her?
I don't know her.
You still helped her get a job?
Well,
I can't say I know her,
but I can't say I don't know her either.
I see. A dangerous situation.
You two could become something one day.
It's a safe situation.
Nothing's safe between a man and a woman.
Having a goalie
doesn't mean the goal's safe.
You're both wearing safety helmets
just for show.
But in your hearts, the sirens wail
and babies cry already.
Why don't you just focus on
writing your script?
Why is it safe? Are you siblings?
It's just…
We've run into each other
in some embarrassing situations.
Why are they going there?
Good times.
Well, I guess…
I'm not going to date anymore.
Especially not the box office girl.
Hey, stop acting like you're all that
and just date more.
This is still cold.
It's a fleeting privilege in a short life.
- You know what?
- What?
- My family doesn't know.
That I'm in Korea.
The plan was to come
at the end of the month,
so they don't know I'm here.
You're such a bad boy.
Should I tell them?
Should I?
Don't you dare.
On the cuteness scale,
you're even cuter than puppies.
DAEHAN NEWS
Hey, man!
Why are you leaving with that on?
I chose this place
because of that thing up there.
Up there, you'll see
the biggest Christmas tree in Korea.
You won't see one that big even in the US.
If I lived too close to the school,
my friends would be over all the time.
Rooms near the school
are always in high demand,
so the landlords are total dictators.
And I love the fact
that meals aren't included here.
I don't eat much anyway.
HELP US FIND OUR MISSING STUDENTS
Geum-myeong.
Yeah?
What is it?
Not here.
Look at this place. It's like Harlem.
People who write stuff like that
on other people's walls
are all sick in the head.
Why would you pick such a dangerous area?
I can't sleep
if you live in an area like this.
Why are they fighting on my way home?
That man's an artist.
He is treasured by our theater.
So stop overreacting.
Who would be okay
with their girlfriend living here?
I'd be crazy not to worry.
What about this neighborhood?
Everyone's doing just fine here.
You should move. Let's go somewhere else.
- What about my neighborhood--
- Where exactly?
What, to your apartment?
You don't really know Seoul--
You're the one who doesn't know Seoul.
You're the one.
I'm saying this
because I'm worried about you.
Just go home.
I'm not showing you where I live.
All of Korea is like Harlem right now.
Serial murders and--
Then go back to America.
Go back, you Yank.
Don't you dare follow me.
I've never seen him smile. Ever.
He keeps his mouth shut all the time.
Even if I tried to strike up
a conversation with him…
You could've just eaten the ones
that were open.
Why do you think he bought the dumplings?
So why did you yell at him again?
You're wasting money on dumplings.
Give them to him yourself.
Our Picasso painted Madame Aema,
but he didn't use any skin-tone paint.
How does that make any sense?
AEMA WANTS TO RIDE AGAIN
MADAME AEMA
How has he still not been fired
after this?
Does he sleep here as well?
BAEK SEOK'S POETRY COLLECTION
ME, NATASHA, AND THE WHITE DONKEY
THOUGH I'M POOR
I LOVED THE BEAUTIFUL NATASHA
SO TONIGHT, THE SNOW WHUMPFS DOWN
Because you're not interested in money?
Because you're a noble artist, right?
I'm not the one who's broke,
so why should I go on about money?
You don't care about money,
so it's all fine?
To be by your side,
I have to think about money all day long.
"How much were the pork cutlet
and tickets?"
Even for a trip, I'd think,
"You have no money. It'd be a burden."
We dated for three years
and never went to a nice restaurant.
Just those stupid kalguksu and jjolmyeon,
over and over.
Dating you makes me a cheap person!
Is that art?
Is that what your art stands for?
How many more times will you come
and vent your anger before your wedding?
Just leave. No need to save face.
You can just go.
You'll just let me go?
- I'm tired too.
- What?
You've been on six blind dates
since we got together.
It's not fair.
I'm done.
I don't think I like you enough anymore
to put up with all the unfairness.
You have someone?
You got a new girl?
Is that why you're acting all tough?
Like you are?
Why aren't you answering?
You have someone,
yet you're acting like the victim.
So what do you want me to do?
If I tell you to stay, will you?
Perhaps it was since then.
My landlord's daughter
started kicking my shoes outside my room.
Well,
I brought you some dumplings.
The projectionist insisted
I bring these to you.
I'm really not sure
why I always run into you
when you are
in these embarrassing situations.
I don't believe this.
PART-TIME USHER
CANNES THEATER
Did you help her get a job here?
Well…
You've been hiding a honeypot
in the theater?
How nice of her.
She even packed food for you.
This is…
Hey.
Why won't you say anything?
You should say something.
I can't believe this.
She'd fit right in with your family.
Can't sort the wheat from the chaff?
You always come up empty.
You dropped out of high school, right?
She goes to SNU.
Watch your words.
The fall breeze turned into
the spring breeze.
The whistling sound
never ceased in my heart.
THE WIND GOES WHOOSH
MY HEART GOES BOO-HOO.
"JUST GET READY AND GO,
RIDE THE MOMENT WITH ALL YOU HAVE."
Subtitle translation by: Sung In Jang