WHEN LIFE GIVES YOU TANGERINES
DAECHI POLICE
Are you a lord?
Are you the judge?
If you hit us, must we take it?
If you send us to Namsan, must we go?
If you say I'm a thief, am I one?
If you send me to jail, must I go?
The ring next to the porcelain jar.
The diamond ring.
I've never even seen a diamond ring!
It's not here.
Who was that female officer?
Was it Yeon-sun?
Tell her to come here
and search this girl.
Yes, sir.
Why would anyone need to search me?
I'm not a thief!
See? You must really be hiding something.
The lady's been turning a blind eye
to this girl taking money from a jar.
- No, I earned that--
- How did you earn it?
You're an illegal tutor, right?
The lady let the girl handle bookkeeping
and overlooked her stealing
because she was a working student.
Do all poor people steal, then?
Some people wouldn't steal
even if beaten into it.
Let us search you, then.
Why do I have to?
I'm not a thief! Why should I have to…
Something's off about you.
What's your home phone number?
I need to see your father.
Why do you need to see my father?
I'm not a thief!
If you have nothing to hide, call him.
Acting like this is a sign of guilt!
If I tell my father
I'm suspected of being a thief,
it will tear his heart apart!
- All buses to the dorms stop here--
- I get it. Leave.
- I'm waiting for my bus home…
- Not heading to the base?
- I'm on leave until Friday.
- Go back early, then.
Sorry?
Don't you dare date Geum-myeong. Got it?
Why won't you answer?
Are you two…
dating?
Are you testing me?
- I got dumped.
- Dumped? You?
I always get dumped.
You're chasing girls instead of studying.
That's why you always get dumped.
Did your dad tell you
to date around in college?
It's not that.
I was dumped eight times by Geum-myeong.
Do you want one or something?
It's okay. You should have it, Father.
Well, Mr. Yang.
Have a safe trip back.
But why?
Why doesn't she like you?
I just think--
It's because you're too…
You're too… You know?
- You're dead meat.
- It's not that--
She grew up watching me,
so her standards are high.
Up until she turned five,
she said she'd marry me when she grew up.
That's why you don't cut it.
So just move on with your life.
There's a lid for every pot.
The reason we're on and off is--
What does "on and off" even mean?
- Well…
- What?
She says I'm as quiet as a mouse
and that I'm not saying anything…
You're as quiet as a mouse.
Why aren't you saying anything?
To be ready.
- You have the ring on, so that's it.
- Ready, go.
Well,
since you offered…
No.
Go away.
You lied about the ring?
She didn't take it, did she?
Goodness gracious.
Why send her to the police?
You usually just frame them and fire them.
Who would believe a thief?
We need to make it seem like
she's spewing nonsense
because she's accused of being a thief
to avoid any trouble later.
If she starts a rumor
that Oh Jenny from Daechi-dong
is looking for someone to take her exam,
you and I will be in deep shit.
My ring was stolen,
and that girl is the thief.
I always tell you, don't I?
Life is all about betting big
or going bust.
Whether I'll crush or be crushed,
that's a split-second decision.
There's no need to pity those
whose wells have run dry.
Don't be swayed by petty sentiments.
You need to be cold.
That's how I made my money.
So keep making good money.
You'll be in for it if your well runs dry.
What?
I take after you.
You're saying
she stole the flower-shaped ring
that's always here, right?
Yeah.
How dare she.
- It's a diamond.
- Yes. Diamond.
How many carats was it?
About half a carat?
Was it half a carat?
It was expensive.
Flower-shaped.
Yes, flower-shaped. Seriously!
What would you even know?
Oh dear, here it is.
It's right over
here.
It just naturally rolled here on its own.
You should call the police, shouldn't you?
Lady, what are you doing?
Call the police
and let them know you found the ring.
Apologize for the mix-up.
I'm asking you what you're doing.
You won't call them?
Lady!
If you don't, I'll throw it away.
You're out of your mind!
Do you have any idea
how expensive that was?
- Come on! Seriously!
- You've lost it anyway, right?
You said it was stolen
and that the girl was the thief.
And now you're going to report
that I've thrown it away?
Damn it!
Put it down!
Don't you know me? I would throw this.
Very far, in fact.
- I'll--
- Hey!
That ring is worth more than you are!
Call them.
Stay out of my fucking business.
Apologize.
Who do you think you are? Stay out of it!
Do you know her?
- I do.
- Seriously! You're driving me insane.
Call them now!
Hello?
What now? Asking for money again?
We don't have any.
Hey, Geum-myeong's mom!
- Your daughter called!
- Okay.
My baby! Oh my!
"Baby"? Seriously?
- Baby! Where are you?
- Baby's somewhere spending money!
I wanted to cry like a baby
and tell her that people in Seoul
were really evil.
Baby, have you eaten?
But that single sentence full of worries
left me speechless.
Who hasn't eaten by now?
My heart melted.
No, I called just because.
Can't I call just because I feel like it?
I do.
I have money.
What about you? Is everything okay?
Didn't I tell you to stop setting up
that stall on the street?
I told you I hate
that you eat out on the street every day!
Those damn abalones! Seriously!
Is abalone season that important?
You always say your back hurts.
Just open a store or something!
You need money to open a store.
Mom.
Why don't you ever have any money?
I know, right?
Why don't I ever have any money?
Because of you!
I was mad at my mom for being poor.
I was mad because I knew I was the reason.
Baby, Dad hasn't arrived yet, has he?
You didn't call
because you met him, did you?
Dad?
Dad received a reward
for saving that person from drowning.
I told you it was happening today.
The governor sent a group of co-op members
to the mainland to go sightseeing.
He gave them museum tickets
because a new one opened.
Where on the mainland? Which museum?
He wants to see you
if he can find the time.
Where on the mainland?
On the mainland.
You know, the museum that just opened.
You always just say "the mainland."
How am I supposed to know where that is?
Which museum is he coming to?
He'll visit if he can find the time?
I'm busy too!
So is Dad coming or not?
Geum-myeong.
He'll be there.
Dad will be there.
- Kim Young-sam!
- Kim Dae-jung!
Gosh, the traffic is awful.
She's actually insane.
How can she accuse you of stealing?
So the cops called your house?
No.
I refused to give them
my home phone number.
- You're not gonna tell your family?
- How could I?
It's okay if the whole world knows,
as long as my mom and dad don't.
Parents have no idea
of the moment
when their child's heart develops knots.
If they knew, they'd protect their child.
So God keeps it from them.
No tree grows without knots,
and a child's knots would carve a hole
in a father's heart,
so God keeps it hidden.
Goodness me.
You'll be the death of me.
I could've been really late!
It's cold. It gets colder at night.
How long have you been waiting for me?
All college students seem to cradle these.
What time did you get here?
Let's go. Come on.
Doesn't this bother you?
Why is your bag strap always twisted?
Did you come to Seoul to eat jjamppong?
Aren't we going to talk?
You drink too.
I can hold my booze.
Well, you're not into protests, are you?
What museum opened?
Where are you staying?
I just stopped by.
Tear gas is so painful.
The tears just won't stop.
Which subway line is it?
Can you get there by yourself?
Well,
you're not dating a soldier, are you?
You shouldn't date one.
Why even eat together if it's like this?
Let's just each talk on our own.
I quit my part-time job.
I was asked to leave the dorms.
I didn't get a scholarship.
It's all good.
This college is full of kids
who aced the state exam.
Basically, all the dragons from streams
have gathered in one puddle.
You can't always be the best.
No one's that perfect.
I wouldn't even share a lunch table
with those kinds of kids.
"A dragon from the stream."
Why do I dislike hearing that?
Who benefits if a dragon rises
from the stream?
Is it any good for the stream?
And what good is it for the dragon?
I was selected to study abroad.
But I just won't go.
I really hate
that Oh Ye-rim is taking my place.
But I just won't go.
I want to study abroad too.
I don't want that damn part-time job.
I want to try everything.
But I'm not going to.
I'm just being greedy.
It's just me being selfish.
I want to soar higher and higher.
But something keeps holding me back.
Mom and I?
No.
Guilt.
The higher I want to soar…
the more guilt holds me back.
Why should I feel bad
for wanting to do something more?
It's so infuriating. I can't take it.
All I ever wanted was to say I'm sorry,
but when those tender words left my lips,
they always turned into barbs.
Geum-myeong.
What?
Do it.
Do it all.
I'm still here for you.
Geum-myeong,
tell your teacher
Dad will pay the school support fees
in three days.
I'm still here for you.
Am I a child?
Why do you keep picking out the squid
and giving it to me?
For the first time in 16 years,
citizens voted in the election,
with 89.2% turnout…
Find a safe place to stay.
No need to worry about the rent at all.
As for the money…
The waters are full of fish.
I can catch them all.
Don't date a soldier.
Don't drink hard liquor.
Don't go to protests.
Tear gas is extremely painful.
You can't stop crying.
Reunification Democratic Party's
Kim Young-sam
voted with his wife, Son Myung-soon.
The news is what scares me the most.
To be honest,
I know nothing.
I don't know anything.
But I can't sleep when I see
soldiers with batons on the news.
Just hearing about college kids
getting taken somewhere and beaten…
Oh man.
It sends shivers down my spine.
So, Geum-myeong,
if you can help it…
Democratic Justice candidate Roh Tae-woo
is in the lead.
Under the slogan
"A great era of ordinary people…"
It's so annoying.
What's wrong?
Did you vote for someone else?
You're annoying.
You're so annoying, Dad.
You call this just stopping by?
You think the whole mainland
is just one place?
Democratic Justice Party's Roh Tae-woo…
You can't come home often.
We're so far apart.
Which museum is he coming to?
He'll visit if he can find the time?
I'm busy too!
So is Dad coming or not?
Geum-myeong, he'll be there.
Dad will be there.
When have you ever seen Dad
go sightseeing?
Even on New Year's or Korean Thanksgiving,
he's eager to take his boat out to sea.
He just used this chance
as an excuse to see you.
But I've got my own things
to do, too, you know?
Dad went
because he really missed his eldest.
So Geum-myeong, when you see your dad…
YONGSAN INTERCITY BUS STATION
Why would he come all the way
from Cheonan to Seoul?
So annoying.
So, Geum-myeong,
when you see your dad,
don't get annoyed with him.
Be sweet to your father, okay?
His love has been one-sided for 20 years.
Catch a lot of fish!
Catch a lot of squids!
Goodness me,
I'm leaving that little thing behind.
Because of his daughter who,
in his eyes, refused to grow up,
Dad thought he might again feel sorry…
for his forever little girl, Ae-sun.
FROM YANG EUN-MYEONG (CLASS 2-7)
How can I put this?
I'm not good at things like this!
Tell the kids who bought the "S" letters
from you to return them.
Just give them the money
and take them back!
They keep saying
they don't have them anymore!
Do you know how much this scotch costs?
Do you know how long it takes
to earn this?
Their fall was…
Harvesting season, my foot.
…not a season of harvest
but of being picked clean.
You pick at me more and more as you age.
My fruit has been picked clean!
HR teacher, Sonata. Principal, Stellar.
Chinese teacher, Pony, right?
- Right?
- Yeah.
Oh, teacher.
Oh, hi.
Hello, sir.
Hello.
It was fall when each was picked clean
of what had been sown.
Is that your booze?
Is that girl your daughter or a relative?
What do you even know?
I know her.
Yes, I'm sure you do.
- I don't need any more free stuff.
- That free stuff--
If you get drunk, they'll rob you.
She said you'll melt like butter, right?
What are you saying?
Don't turn the lights off, no matter what.
That woman is a real thief.
If you fall asleep, she'll steal your bag.
Why tell me this?
- Sorry?
- Why are you telling me?
Why did you help me?
Why did you even bother?
Do you know me?
What am I to you?
Why?
It'd be upsetting.
It'd be upsetting
if your bag got stolen too.
Is that all?
It's better if none of us are upset.
You're right.
It'd be upsetting
if the girl got wrongly accused of theft.
You might as well be Mother Teresa.
You don't know that girl.
Do you even know SNU?
You've always been so nosy.
I do know her.
She protected my mom's inheritance
when I was young.
That girl wasn't even born then!
- She's the spitting image of that girl.
- My goodness.
If you weren't my old bar boss,
I'd have already…
What?
You'd make me a thief and fire me too?
Miss Kim.
Ma'am.
Stop calling me "Miss Kim"
in front of my daughter.
Why live such a shameful life
if you're scared of your kid's judgment?
Your daughter is watching everything.
Damn it! I told you to throw away
the empty ones!
Live a life of virtue, I'm telling you.
The parents' virtues and karma
go straight to the child.
Look at her.
You can tell
she's already on the wrong path.
I know.
My mom made me do it.
SEOUL STATION
How can I leave when you look like this?
Then don't leave!
Are we back together, then?
I don't know. Just stay still for now.
Stop breaking my heart.
I might end up becoming a deserter.
How many days are left?
797 days.
I hate North Korea so much!
I can't do much
about our on-and-off relationship.
But just marry me in the end, okay?
It depends.
On how well you do.
You said you'd marry me last time.
Hey, who knows what will happen?
They say you don't know
until you walk down the aisle.
Just wait and see.
I'll see you in a wedding dress.
I truly believed I was different from Mom.
Hey, are you getting on or what?
In the end,
it was like mother, like daughter,
though not entirely.
The bride will now enter
and walk down the aisle.
Geum-myeong.
Dad's still right here.
Just do everything you want to do.
Mom's love was a fairy tale.
Please welcome the bride.
Will my story also be a fairy tale?
'67 THE 7TH HALLA CHUNSA FESTIVAL
Ice pops!
- Here, enjoy.
- Thank you.
Ice pops!
THEME
JEJU, SPRING BREEZE, WIND
"Jeju."
"By Oh Ae-sun
from Dodong Girls' High, class 1-5."
Ten million waves
Ten million winds
Yet a rock still stands
A rock that never erodes
In the sea of my heart
Mom.
I told you not to sit next to me.
Go back to your side!
What's an athlete doing
in the writing contest? Who sent you here?
I raised my hand
and said I wanted to enter.
You know what they say around town?
They say Gwan-sik wakes up
just to follow Ae-sun around.
I think you'll be the winner this time.
I think you'll be a great poet.
A great poet.
- Really?
- Yes.
What would you know?
I don't.
I can't write.
I should write to the Ministry.
They need to make athletes study too.
Will they take responsibility
for this kid's life?
SPRING BREEZE
I'm so upset, seriously.
THE WIND GOES WHOOSH
MY HEART GOES BOO-HOO
Erase the moth. Why did you draw it here?
It's a butterfly.
Write a poem for me too.
Titled "Yang Gwan-sik."
Why would I?
In life, you never know what will happen
unless you go for it.
Who knew I'd still be sitting here
20 years later?
THE 28TH HALLA CHUNSA WRITING CONTEST
THEME
SPRING, WIND, MOON
Submit this.
FALL BREEZE
OH AE-SUN
I'm not in high school anymore.
The paper was lying on the ground,
so I scribbled a few lines.
I still think you should submit it.
Submit what? Forget it.
Tomorrow's sports day is canceled too.
Why?
They're rehearsing for the Olympics too.
We earn the most on sports days.
We should set up our own place,
even if it means going into debt.
I'm sick and tired of
this bundle-carrying life.
Excuse me.
Hello. Would you like some mini snails?
Ae-sun? You're Oh Ae-sun, right?
It's Chang-suk. Go Chang-suk.
We went to high school together.
Oh, Chang-suk.
It's been ages.
I haven't seen you since you left school.
The others are wondering how you're doing.
You don't even attend school reunions.
Don't you get those?
The reunion postcards?
Maybe you're not on the list
because you dropped out?
I'll just give this to you for free.
I'll give you plenty.
Gosh, she can't even look.
Why? Is she embarrassed
about getting expelled?
No, not her high school friend.
Mom could never bear
to look at kids that age.
Hey, it's not here.
How old are you?
Fifteen.
Fifteen, born in the Year of the Tiger.
Yes.
Here it is.
Hey, where?
Is that popular these days?
- Sorry?
- What else is popular?
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
Sure, enjoy them all.
Yes, sir.
In Dad's heart,
Dong-myeong was still growing up.
I believe sympathy is part of evolution.
Look at the old women in the countryside.
They're fine after losing their kids.
They'd say,
"I had eight kids and two died."
"You had a brother once,"
as if it were nothing.
How can they?
How do you go on after losing a child?
But they carry on just fine.
What are they supposed to do?
Cry every day? Starve?
No, the point of our presentation
is to prove the correlation
between sympathy and civilization.
Right?
Are they below you?
What?
You think they are like that
because they're lesser than you?
Just keep playing with your eraser.
It's not because
they're not as admirable as you.
They don't act like nothing's wrong
because they're less evolved.
They move on because they have to.
Geum-myeong, I'm sorry to say this.
Do you feel inferior to me?
Why would I be?
Well, for several reasons.
You even lost your chance to study abroad.
Did I lose it? I'm just letting you go.
Letting me go?
Then you should go.
You can go.
You keep acting like you're letting me go,
but you don't get to go
just because your GPA is higher.
Family background
and circumstances count too.
Who said that?
Your father again?
Life's about the total score in the end.
I'm the one who got 37 votes.
So what if you got 37 votes?
Do your 37 votes matter now?
In real life,
37 votes don't mean anything!
Between you and Man-ki,
there's something that goes
beyond just nine votes, okay?
Take it.
Yeah, here. Take it.
Leave it here. Take one.
Man-ki's dad brought these
to celebrate him becoming president.
He treated you last time, right?
You should feel guilty
if you took a bun and didn't vote for him.
If you have to stay behind,
you'll get one only after you're done.
Yeah, take one.
Take one.
DIARY
OH AE-SUN
Man-ki! Are you even studying properly?
You're not just eating cream buns
at home, are you?
Our class president is a fake president.
He's a cream bun president.
Even if he has 100 cream buns,
Lee Man-ki will never get 100 points.
But I got 100 points.
Mom was like a wildflower
that finds its way to the sunlight,
even if it was under a dark brick wall.
Let's hurry.
In the end,
she would always find the light.
Careful.
This is where I was set up on a date
with Bu Sang-gil back in the day.
At the time,
I really thought my life was over.
I heard you really wanted
a man from Seoul.
I'm pretty much from Seoul.
Right after Korea's liberation,
my wealthy family sent me
to study in Seoul.
If I hadn't married and moved down here,
I could've been a man of power.
At the beginning of my first marriage…
Am I getting that tea anytime today?
Don't worry about what I think.
Love isn't…
Goodness.
Who would've thought I'd own this place?
As I said, in life, you never know
what will happen unless you go for it.
Go!
I even thought of the name of this place.
That's right.
The shop name should be chosen
by someone well-educated.
"Sun and the Three Aunties'."
Why bother with a complicated name?
Even poetry collections sell better
with a simple title.
This land has thousands of people
with "Sun" in their names,
so attracting them would be enough, right?
Yeah, that's right.
- Your name gets top billing.
- Let her do it.
Let's stop having lunch on the street.
From now on,
I'm only eating at the dining table.
You eat at the table.
So each of us gets a quarter, okay?
Ae-sun, you just pay this much.
We'll cover the rest.
The water pressure is low.
What?
The water pressure…
This is enough. You can wash
sea cucumbers and sea squirts with it.
I'll wash them all.
However, while the faucet barely dripped,
steady and diligent,
the leaking hole was gushing relentlessly.
ELIGIBILITY FOR STATE-FUNDED STUDY ABROAD
I just find it funny
that an English major is going to Japan.
It also means I'll graduate later,
so I probably shouldn't…
I don't think I should…
I… want you to go.
Ye-rim is a bit…
snobbish.
Since you don't qualify
for the state-funded scholarship,
as I mentioned before…
Oh no, please don't do that.
I'm going to leave.
I won't come back if you call me again.
Come on. I'm quite well off, you know?
You can pay me back later.
You said your car was the cheapest
in the faculty parking lot.
It's not the time to be worrying about me.
Be brazen at times like this!
Or you'll end up like me.
But you're really amazing.
I think you're the only professor
who gives apples to sparrows.
I'm truly grateful
that you are looking out for me.
I feel like I've already been to Japan.
Even your words are pretty.
When I spoke to others,
it was as if I were writing a love letter.
I would choose my words carefully,
one by one.
Yeah, she's such a great person.
A really great person.
When others treat you well,
even just once, they become your savior.
Yeah, so you have to send
the best tangerines you can find.
She's so good to me.
So what does she do for you?
Does she say she likes you
or you're doing well?
What did she say?
I want to hear it and feel happy too!
She wants to lend me money
so I can study abroad.
It's not easy to do for others.
She takes only me to the faculty cafeteria
and buys me lunch.
But you said
you didn't really want to study abroad.
Just send a box of tangerines.
Do you want to study abroad?
You want to go?
So what if I want to go?
Can I even go?
How much is it?
Come on, how much is it?
You don't need to know.
I'm not saying I'll pay for it.
Just tell me approximately how much.
Mom, don't you watch TV?
The yen is crazy high now.
But you could at least tell me
the approximate cost.
You're really starting to make me mad.
Are you a beggar? Don't you have parents?
Why would others offer to lend you money?
What on earth are you doing?
You think I look like
I'm from a wealthy family?
I'm not going to Japan,
so everyone knows we're not well-off.
So how much is it?
Just tell me how much it is!
And what if I tell you? You gonna send me
with money from the stall?
If you have the money,
stop selling at the stall!
Gosh, I want to stop too. I really do.
But how can I?
Whatever, just forget it.
Don't bother sending the tangerines.
Talking to you is just so annoying.
But I treated the savior
to whom I'm a million times grateful
like scrap paper.
What now?
I wasn't careful
with my words or my feelings.
I'm not eligible whatsoever.
How much is it?
Just 300 won. Give me 300 won.
How much for all of it?
Huh?
I like beans.
A kind-hearted mother
gave birth to a kind-hearted daughter.
They would always adore each other
and break each other's hearts.
I want to stop selling on the street too.
Who in the world
wants to make a living as a street vendor?
I used to be coy as well.
I used to get called Literary Girl.
When I run into a high school friend
while eating on newspaper in the market,
I just want to stop eating.
I lose my appetite for the whole day.
Is she the only one with pride?
Am I like this because I lack it?
But what can I do?
She has so many things she wants to do,
and not being able to help
kills me inside.
Strange how you started asking for liquor
after seeing your beloved daughter.
You know,
I have nothing to say to you or her.
My mom must've cried her eyes out
when I didn't become class president
due to mental and financial limitations.
I only get it now.
What did she say?
Did she cry about wanting to study abroad?
She cried out of frustration, right?
For the daughter who would never grow up,
they ended up selling that house.
These are the last persimmons, right?
Eat them all. Don't give any away.
Not even to our kids?
Not even to our kids.
Only you can eat them.
The more the kids grow,
the more they pick us clean, right?
Didn't you know
this was a losing business?
They left behind the house
where Ae-sun's mother, little Ae-sun…
and the one whose name they dared not say,
Dong-myeong, would be missed.
Mom, I didn't realize how young you were.
You need to get rid of the chipped ones!
You visited my dream when we moved here.
Are you back because we're leaving?
You're so stingy.
You should've visited my dreams more.
Mom, I'm upset.
I have so much I want to say to my mom.
What's the point of writing that?
He can't even read.
He didn't learn to read.
How can he read it?
Just in case he comes over here
during the holidays
and is surprised Mommy isn't here.
I didn't want to scare the baby.
Do you and Gwan-sik
still never talk about him?
Don't you talk to him about Dong-myeong?
Why would we?
We already know how each other feels.
Any other grief fades with time
and becomes numb.
But when the grief is too deep,
when it's too deep,
I end up burying it.
I just can't bring it up.
Ae-sun.
Talk to him.
Pour it all out.
Even the deep ocean
uses the waves
to pour out restlessly.
I'm sorry to say this to you.
I know it's not fair,
but I can bear to reminisce about you.
Not my baby though.
It's not possible with a child.
All I wanted was
for you to have a good life.
How will my baby go on?
How has my baby survived the pain?
I just forget briefly from time to time.
Just from time to time.
Somehow, life goes on.
THE MOON WANES,
YET THE YOUNG HEART REMAINS.
Tomorrow…
Hurry, this way.
…life will go on
under the blazing sun of tomorrow.
Careful.
Damn those planes.
Why are there so many of them?
Ladies and gentlemen,
we are now arriving
at New Tokyo International Airport.
- Hey, can you empty this ashtray?
- Yes, sir.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we are now arriving
at New Tokyo International Airport.
The local time is 11:50 a.m.
Why did she wrap it over and over?
Why did she wrap it like this?
Seriously.
Have some, crybaby.
Thank you.
No problem.
I swallowed their dreams
and spread my wings,
embracing my mom's dream
like a seed in my heart.
Is this funny? Is this funny to you?
That damn studying…
How I really wanted to do it so badly.
But now my daughter
is even going to study abroad.
It's so thrilling, isn't it?
How fantastic is that?
So are you happy?
Mom!
Mom's dream was passed on to me…
a dream so heavy, a dream so blazing…
When you guys soar,
I swear it feels like I'm soaring too.
…that, at last,
it made the sound of wings flapping.
WHEN LIFE GIVES YOU TANGERINES
DODONG GIRLS' HIGH
Did you get Ae-sun's permission?
Why limit writing contests to kids?
Sauces taste better when fermented.
One knows life better after living it.
Kids don't know life's thorns and burdens.
Once again,
if there is a student named Oh Ae-sun,
please come to the faculty office
immediately.
Oh Ae-sun.
When the students are taking tests,
there are always some students
who never write their grade and class,
no matter how many times you remind them.
Did I or did I not tell you
that you must tell them countless times?
Did I or did I not?
Am I talking to a wall?
The winner is from our school,
and we can't find the student.
What am I supposed to tell the principal?
Goodness gracious.
EVEN AS I GENTLY PRESS MY HEART
TO SOOTHE IT DOWN
THE MOON WANES,
YET THE YOUNG HEART REMAINS.
"IN THE HOPE THAT OUR ECHOES
WILL FLOW AND FLOW UNTIL THEY REACH YOU."
Subtitle translation by: Sung In Jang