Oz 1-6
To Your Health
Six percent of the total prison
population is 55 and older.
That's double ten years ago.
And we say 55 is old because...
...criminal life adds about
ten years worth of wrinkles.
Still, in Oz, you get decent food,...
...exercise, regular check ups.
And if you don't get whacked you live
longer than you would in your own hood.
Yeah, the prison system.
It can keep you alive,...
...but it can't take care of you.
I'm telling you, we're
ignoring the problem.
We have to deal differently
with aging inmates.
That's right. Oz was designed to punish
the young, to keep them in line,...
to keep them down, but
with a guy like Rebadow,...
you don't need to keep him down.
So what are you proposing?
Tell unit 2 into a cell
block exclusively for seniors.
They sleep together there, they can
eat all their meals together there,...
...they can play cards, they can
watch the TV shows they wanna watch.
Saturday night Bingo?
Well, why not? We need
to keep them active.
And less stress will help slow
down the aging process which...
...will help save on medical costs.
Plus, the older guys are not a security
problem, so you can save money on the officers.
McManus, you've been
awfully quiet today.
Never thought I'd ask but do
you have an opinion on this?
Sure. Sounds like a good idea.
-That's it?
-Yep.
Fine, I'll run it by the
Commissioner. Meeting adjourned.
Finally.
Tim, you ok? You don't look so good.
Are you feeling all right?
- I said yeah,...
...ok?
Ok.
Free for dinner tonight?
Dinner?
- You think I'm an asshole.
- I do not think...
Well, I appreciate the offer, but the last
thing I need from you is a mercy dinner.
- Bob Rebadow's in the hospital, Kenny.
- So?
- So, I'm pissed off about that!
- So I hear you're responsible
- Where'd you hear that from?
I got ears everywhere,
Kenny, and I know it's true.
You don't hit old men,
Kenny. You don't...
What do you want, McManus?
You see those guys out there?
If I tell 'em to, they
will gladly kick your ass.
I'm not afraid of them. I'm
not afraid of you either.
- You're not?
- No.
- What are you afraid of?
- I ain't afraid of nothing!
- Nothing?
- Nothing!
Huh, you afraid of this?
You afraid of dying? You
little fucking punkass!
Get him the fuck out of here!
Leo, what are you doing here?
Same thing you are, I guess. I like
to work out when no one else is around.
I'll ignore you if you ignore me.
McManus, you ok?
Why does everybody keep asking me that?
I don't know. Past few weeks
you've seemed different.
I'm fine.
Commissioner rejected our proposal
for a senior citizens unit.
Big surprise. Commissioner
didn't reject it.
Governor Fuckwad did.
Well, Devlin's almost out of office.
I mean, he's on trial for taking those
kickbacks, lying, fraud, extortion.
I'll miss him.
You know, I've been hearing rumors that
you're living in Emerald City,
that you never leave the grounds
to go home anymore.
Since when do you listen to gossip?
You know, I've been dancing
down these hallways a long time.
I've seen this place
change people completely,...
...not just the prisoners.
You're not careful, Tim,...
...Oz'll nick away at your soul.
Huh. That's the first time
you've ever called me Tim.
You know, you don't even
have to be 55 to be old.
How you feeling?
I can't stay here anymore.
- In the hospital?
- In Oz.
- Why?
- I'm afraid.
- Of what?
- Them. The young.
When I first came to Oz, we
treated our elders with dignity.
But these kids, it's all different
now. I've decided to leave.
- Leave?
- Escape.
- How you gonna do that?
- God will show me the way.
The human body. It's amazing.
Made up of all these cells and
neutrons and veins and shit like that.
So many little pieces, so many
things that could break down,
and add on to that the wear...
...and tear we give our bodies,...
...what with the drugs and
drinking and chicken fried steak.
Man, that any of us are still standing,
still breathing, it's a miracle.
Breakfast, boys!
Let's go, Alvarez.
- I think maybe we got a problem.
- What?
Look at Alvarez.
Hey, Alvarez.
You think he's faking?
Alvarez! Alvarez!
Call for the doctor.
Prisoner number 43A515, Ricardo Alvarez.
Convicted March 3, '43. Armed robbery
Sentence: 20 years.
Convicted June 6, '61.
Murder in the first degree.
Sentence: life imprisonment,
solitary confinement.
Ricardo, we're going to
start with a series of tests.
You have to go home?
Your mother? Ricardo, where are you?
Do you know what city you're in?
R. Alvarez: Havana. Havana.
So, we're agreed, the medication's
controlling Cragen's paranoia.
Yeah, we should keep him on it.
Definitely.
Next is Miguel Alvarez.
Oh, yeah. I'm scheduled to do a
psychiatric reevaluation on Thursday.
Good luck, Pete. His baby
died right after birth.
He's pretty depressed.
He's about to become
even more depressed.
His grandfather, Ricardo
Alvarez, has Alzheimer's.
- Christ.
- Does his family know?
No, not yet.
Ricardo's son Eduardo
is an orderly in my ward.
I'll tell him when he
comes in for his shift.
- Eduardo. That's the one with
no tongue, right? - Uh-huh.
I'll talk to Miguel.
Listen, Tim, could I do
that? If you don't mind.
I'm always willing to give up an
opportunity to deliver bad news.
Next?
- Miguel, I need you to come with me.
- I didn't do shit!
Miguel, please.
Come on.
How come no one knew 'til now
that Ricardo's mind was going?
He was in solitary, Miguel. He hardly
says three words a day to anyone.
And there's nothing we could have
done to stop the disease anyway.
So what happens now?
Well, that's the tricky part.
Unfortunately, Oz is just not equipped...
...for long term custodial care and
there isn't anywhere else to send him.
You're telling me the state doesn't have
anyplace to take care of its old prisoners?
The state, the state's attitude
towards the elderly,
any elderly, in or out of prison
is hurry up and die.
I wanna see my grandfather.
Hey.
It's me, Miguel, and Eduardo.
Eduardo, your son.
Miguel, grandson.
You know what we should
do with Ricardo Alvarez?
What's that?
Let him go free.
Let him go free? The man
is a convicted killer.
He stabbed the inmate who
cut his son's tongue out.
- And he's old.
- He's old, Leo.
Old doesn't necessarily mean nice.
If there's any doubts about that,
spend ten minutes with my mother in law.
Leo, a 31 year old inmate
costs $21000 a year to maintain.
A senior costs three times that amount.
Since when did you get so
interested in the budget?
Since I figured out that the money we're gonna
waste taking care of Ricardo Alvarez could...
...be put to much better use.
Besides, Ricardo
doesn't know where he is
or why he's here. There is such a
thing as criminal menopause, right?
He cannot commit the crime again.
The man is no longer
a threat to anybody.
It doesn't change what he did and
it doesn't change his sentence.
Life imprisonment means just that.
Besides, if he doesn't really know he's in
prison, then he's already free. Isn't he?
When I was growing up, both my
father and my grandfather came to Oz.
You know, when I was little I always
wondered what was so great about prison
that they'd wanna leave us to come here.
But you're a kid. What do you know?
Yeah. So, the word "grandfather". What
does the word mean to you? Emotionally?
Nothing. Don't mean
nothing at all to me.
Pizza means more. Doorknob.
Would you like Grandfather
to mean something to you?
Yeah.
Dr. Nathan's not sure how long
your grandfather has to live. Look,
since your father's an orderly
in the hospital and is going to
spend the remaining time
with your grandfather,
there's no reason you
can't do the same thing.
Maybe if you take care of him,
you'll learn to care for him.
You know, in my family, Ricardo was
like God. You know, he was a legend.
My grandmother used to show me these pictures,
you know, and tell me stories all about him.
And I wanted to be like him, you know.
Now I see he's just a man, you know. He's
just an old man and he's rotting away.
- I don't wanna end up like my grandfather.
- You don't have to, Miguel.
Oh, really? Well, I don't see
it going down any other way.
Rebadow, I'm sorry
you didn't make it out.
It's ok. It was worth it.
The adrenaline rush. I felt 25 again.
Here's your dinner.
- I don't want it.
- OK. What do you want?
I'd like a few years at the
end of my life to be free.
Do we care for people when they're sick
because we actually care about them?
Or do we care for them because when our
time comes, we want someone to care for us?
Or does it matter?
At least you got your health.
Don't you hate it when people say that?
I mean, you lose your job, you
lose your wife, you're in prison,
and some punkass dude gonna say,
"At least you got your health."
Like that's supposed
to make me feel better.
So what if I'm broke? So what if
some drug dealer wants to cap my ass?
At least I ain't got a tumor.
I swear, the next person
that says ALYGYH to me,
I'm gonna make sure they ain't
got their health much longer.
You say you were having nightmares.
Can you remember any of them?
- No. Ow.
- What's the matter?
My tooth hurts. It's
been hurting for a week.
- Then go see a dentist.
- No.
- Why?
- I hate the dentist.
All dentists, or just
Dr. Cocher in particular?
The concept of dentists.
Then what? You prefer
the concept of pain?
Make an appointment, Groves? OK? OK.
- Oh, God.
- What?
- Oh, sweet Jesus, Donald Groves
is coming in to see me. - So?
Gloria, he ate his parents.
I'm not sticking my fingers in his
mouth. My fingers are my livelihood.
He's been working in the ward
as an orderly. He seems harmless.
- So you'd stick your fingers
in his mouth? - If I had to.
- If he's in pain, you have to.
- No, I don't.
What about the Hippocratic Oath?
Dentists don't take the Hippocratic Oath.
We don't make any promises to anybody.
How's that gas working?
- You feel happy?
Calm? - Uh-huh.
Good. OK, let's have a look.
Open your mouth.
Wider. Wider. Wider.
I can't get any wider.
- Allrighty, then. They look fine.
- It hurts.
- It's probably nothing.
- It's hurts.
- Oh, don't be a baby.
- Who are you calling a baby?
Nobody. Forget it.
Forget I said anything.
A-ha. There is a tooth that's rotted
out. I'm going to have to pull it.
That means I have to get a needle and
inject some Novocaine in your mouth.
- I hate needles.
- Everybody does.
- Then I have to drill.
- I hate drills.
Right now, so do I. Right now I
wish there were holistic dentistry.
I'm in pain.
Well, you're going to be in a
lot more before we're finished.
After that, you won't have any pain.
If I cause you pain it's not my
fault, so don't bite my head off.
- I mean, uh...
- I know what you mean.
OK. Let's get started. First,
the Novocaine. Open wide.
Carol, could you give
me a hand here, please?
This is my tooth. It was in my head.
This tooth and I have been
together since we were kids.
This tooth chewed on my mom.
- You should sell it.
- Sell it? - Sell it.
The tooth from the
mouth of Donald Groves?
- Do you know how much that's worth
on the open market? - How much?
- Plenty.
- Who'd wanna buy my tooth?
- Collectors.
- Collectors?
Collectors. People collect everything.
Stamps, salt and pepper
shakers, World's Fair tchochkes.
Some people collect crime stuff.
Lindbergh ladder, Ted
Bundy's toenail clippings,
and this.
We'd have to get a fence, right?
We're in prison. How
hard's that gonna be?
Ross, if we get a good price,
I still got 30 more.
The mind is just like the body.
It's under constant assault from fear
and hate and a whole pile of loneliness.
These things are as
deadly as any Cancer cell.
The mind is just like the body.
The fact that the mind
can survive is a miracle.
All right, yo! All right!
Our next contestant is the lovely
and talented Tobias Beecher.
Never treats me sweet and
gentle, the way he should
I got it bad and that ain't good
When the weekend's over
and Monday rolls around
I end up like I start
out, crying my heart out
He don't love me like I love him
Nobody could
I got it bad and that ain't good
We knew Beecher was doing drugs.
Yeah, but now I'm
beginning to figure it out.
He thinks of himself as a victim,
so he's not going to get better unless
he feels he can control his life.
He's in prison, Peter Marie.
His life is totally out of his control.
I know, but now we have to get
him back to when he was in charge.
We have to remind him that there's
another victim involved here,
the little girl he killed.
Hello.
My husband wouldn't come.
He said he was afraid he might kill you.
This is Kathy.
I'm sorry, I didn't want...
I'm not sure why I came.
At the trial, I was sitting behind you.
I could barely see your face.
Guess I just wanted to finally see you,
see your eyes and to
tell you that I miss her.
Every single moment of every single day.
You fucking bastard!
I hope you die in here, you monster!
I hope you rot in hell!
You killed my baby!
I don't know.
Maybe I let Schillinger
treat me like dirt
because I deserve to be punished.
Because I killed Kathy Rockwell.
Because I destroyed her family.
- And my own.
- And you hate yourself for that?
Yes.
I guess I hated myself back before too.
I hated myself so I drank too much.
I hated myself for drinking too much
so to punish myself, I drank more.
Sister,
I don't wanna hate me anymore.
Hey, don't think you're fooling me.
I know the only way you got through
that variety show was by using drugs.
- Look, I... - Hey, I told you,
I don't want you doing that shit.
I'm sorry, sir.
No, I'm sorry.
Here. Put it on.
Perfect fit. No, no, leave it on.
Come on. If I go out there with this on,
one of those black guys is gonna kill me.
Yeah, I know.
What is this?
There's a new kid in town.
OK, that's great. I'm happy for you.
-  I'll move out of the pod.
- No.
Why not?
I don't want some
nigger to have your ass.
Goodbye, prag.
- O'Reily, I need your help.
- I'm here.
Schillinger wants me dead.
He just gave me this to wear.
What am I gonna do, man?
Well, if you gotta go, you
gotta go high. Ever tried PCP?
The trial of James Devlin opened
today at the state courthouse,
not far from the capital building, where the Governor
has ruled with an iron fist for the past year.
Devlin, who said he'll never
resign even if convicted,
is facing 25 years in prison for fraud, extortion,
racketeering, and obstruction of justice.
Yeah, motherfucker!
That's it! I'm sorry, sir!
Beecher, get down!
God damn, fucking bastard!
Beecher! Beecher! Beecher! Beecher!
Help me!
We need you to keep your
hands away from your face.
Oh, shit.
I need a couple of 4x4's and some tape.
The glass in his eye is pretty
bad. I'm not sure we can save it.
We need to get him to Benchley Memorial
for surgery as soon as possible.
Fuck, I'm gonna kill that motherfucker.
Beecher, you're a dead man!
- You have to go back to drug counseling.
- Fuck off!
If you don't, I'll transfer
you out of Emerald City.
Fuck off!
- Tobias, we're trying to help you.
- Fuck off!
Look, if you're afraid Schillinger's gonna kill
you, I'll place you under protective custody.
Fuck off, fuck off, fuck off,
fuck off, fuck off, you fucks!
People say, "She broke my heart."
That's bullshit, man.
The heart can't break, it's a muscle.
Muscles tear, muscles cramp.
Yeah, the heart's a
muscle. So's the brain.
So's the dick.
O'Reily, give this guy the mop.
You're through with the bucket brigade.
Good.
Dino Ortolani ran the
kitchen like a Swiss watch.
The best. Joey was good. Markstrom too.
But this Adebisi character, he's not
really focused on the job, you know.
And he abuses the
privilege. Everybody steals,
but he steals too much.
Now you're a smart guy and you've been very
efficient doing the jobs I've asked you to do,
so I'm putting you in charge
of the whole cafeteria.
What are you talking?
I run this kitchen.
And you're doing a half-assed job.
I got rotten fruit. I got cold entrees.
I got Glynn complaining
about cost overages.
I'm not working with him.
Fine. How's about I have you
transferred back to the sweatshop?
- I don't like the sweatshop.
- Then shut the fuck up. OK?
It's all yours.
All right, ladies, back to work.
What?
We had a deal. We were partners.
We still are. When it comes to running tits, that
part of the operation I got no complaints with,
but the kitchen I can't
afford you fucking up.
O'Reily will do a good job.
Fuck that pretty little mick.
Adebisi, you make your peace
with this any way you can.
I say O'Reily's gonna run the
kitchen as good as Dino ever did.
You wanna bet on that?
- What the fuck is going on here,
Wangler? - Nothing.
Exactly. Pick up the Goddamned pace!
We're going as fast as we can, man.
You're not fooling me.
What are you talking about, boss?
This. Adebisi, listen to me, I know
why Schibetta put me in charge over you.
He's doing the old divide and conquer.
As long as he keeps the two of us at each
other's throats, he's got all the power.
What are you doing?
Let's face it, the both of
us only got one goal in mind
and that's to take over
Schibetta's drug trade.
- Together we can do it.
- Together?
We gotta make him think
that we're enemies,
keep him off guard 'til we kill him.
We kill him, the mob kills us.
They won't know. Not if
we put this in his food.
Glass.
As long as we make it fine,
he won't be able to taste it.
Over time, the glass
will cut his insides up.
- And he'll die slowly.
- Painfully.
You are a sick motherfucker, O'Reily.
Coming from you, that's a compliment.
- Wangler!
- What's up?
Bring me Schibetta's food.
And tell everyone to
start working full speed.
OK. Everyone, move your asses now!
So, Ryan, if you were released
from Oz today, what would you do?
- Travel.
- Where?
Around. You know, since I got here I've
been reading brochures and vacation guides.
They're great for when you're taking a shit
or before you go to sleep.
While I'm sleeping I actually dream about
going to these places.
- Like?
- Mora Goro.
Mora Goro? That's a jungle, isn't it?
- Yeah. You knew that?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it's in Africa.
- You wanna go with me?
- Me?
Yeah, you and me, you know.
I'm twice your age and I'm a nun.
Yeah, well, growing up and going to
St. Pat's, I never had a nun like you.
St. Pat's, huh? Tough neighborhood.
Yeah, I learned the
alphabet the hard way.
DEA, HIV, IOU.
I see.
You know, Sister, I got 12 years to my
parole. I wanna be alive to make that parole.
I'm gonna walk out of
here. I'm gonna survive.
Nine of Spades.
Trump.
- You ok, Nino?
- Yeah, just a little (?).
I told you, you're making
the red sauce too spicy.
I don't know what the fuck you're
putting in it but it's too fucking spicy.
- Trump.
- Shit.
I was addicted to crack.
Then I had my accident.
Lying in the hospital bed, I went
through detox. But that was easy.
The doctors had me on
Morphine, Demerol, Percodan.
I didn't know I was in pain.
I didn't know I was in
the hospital, paralyzed.
Then I came here, went into counseling.
I take it one day at a time, you know.
But every day I think about drugs.
About not doing drugs.
Every single day, every single
hour, every single minute,
staying straight has become
my obsession. My new addiction.
Oh, shit. Jackson Vayhue got 12 years.
Yeah, I hear he's coming to Oz.
Hey, McManus, I been waiting to see you, man. You
really outta get wheelchair access to your office.
Put it in the suggestion box.
- Hey, I wanna be Jackson Vayhue's sponsor.
- How come?
The man is one of the greatest b-ball players
of all time. I'm one of his biggest fans.
What makes you think that I'm
bringing him to Emerald City?
Cause, like everybody
else, you're a starfucker.
Oh, right. Nobody could ever
accuse you of being an asskisser.
- All right, you're Jackson Vayhue's sponsor.
- When does he arrive?
- Tomorrow.
- Great.
You think you can get the
marching band ready by then?
No!
Prisoner number 97V588, Jackson Vayhue.
Convicted August 17, '97.
Attempted rape, assault.
Sentence: 12 years. Up for parole in 5.
Vayhue, you wait here
for transport to Em City.
The rest of you scumfucks, now that you had
your shower and you're all sweet
and squeaky clean, are gonna follow
Officer Smith to your new accomodations.
This way. Right through there.
Come on, come on, come on.
Hey, Jackson, can I get your
autograph? It's for my kid.
Hey, Jackson, what up, baby?
Nice shot, yo. Thought
I'd find you here.
- I told you to leave me the fuck alone.
- I'm just here to help you get adjusted.
What, adjusted to this shit?
- Where you from? You from the projects?
- Yeah.
Yeah, me too. Spent all your time adjusting,
right? Figuring out how to fucking stay alive.
Figuring out why you don't have nothing.
You got about three ways to get out. You can
sell drugs, sing, or this shit right here.
It all takes talent, man.
I just happened to be lucky.
Fucking joke. I could hang, I
could put this ball in the hoop.
Oh, I got adjusted. I
got famous, I got rich.
I got used to the touring,
the endorsements, the women.
Maybe not the women.
I fucking blew that, boy, I blew that.
The one thing I'm good at
don't mean dick in here.
So how the fuck am I
supposed to adjust to that?
- Fuck you. I ain't doing this.
- Oh, yes, you are.
- What's the story here?
- Mr. NBA won't do his work assignment.
It was explained to you, right?
Everybody in Em City has a job to do.
Give me another job, then,
'cause I'm not doing this one.
You don't get to choose.
Look, pal, I don't do windows,
ok? I don't do windows.
Well, now you get to clean that up.
George Washington Carver.
He was born to slave parents
but he worked his way up and through
Iowa State College,
becoming a botanist and an agricultural chemist.
Now, he discovered hundreds of uses
for the peanut,
the sweet potato, and the soybean. Now...
Mr Vayhue, are you listening to me?
Sure. Soybeans.
All right, we'll pick up here next week.
Vayhue,
I know you're a big
hotshot basketball star.
If you don't start paying attention
in the class, you'll go on report.
Go ahead, nigger.
Oh, no, my friend, you're the nigger.
- You got any drugs?
- No.
Then what the fuck good are you?
- Hey, Jackson, we made this
special for you. - Thanks, man.
No, thank you. I won 10
grand on that Bulls game.
What, you're looking for an autograph?
No, my brother, your
fame means nothing to me.
Except that you are important to many
children and you are a role model.
I didn't ask to be
nobody's fucking role model.
Nonetheless, you are. And that
carries an enormous responsibility.
Look, man, fuck you, all right? Go
preach that shit to somebody else.
All right, my brother, all right.
- But we will talk again.
- Don't bet on that.
- Asalaam aleikuum.
- Eat me, nigger.
Who do you have to fuck to get high?
Son, come on son.
Let me squeeze them titties.
I been fiending for this freedom.
I been begging for the beat.
I been jonesing for
the jump over the wall.
But all I keep coming
back to is them titties.
Round and firm, for the vein burn.
I keep bugging over the reasons.
For this shit I yearn.
Years in this piece got me.
Wanting the shit that I unlearned.
Got me wanting to block it out.
Forget about. Erase it from my think.
Come here, brother.
No.
- What, you don't wanna get titillated?
- No.
Come here, boy, don't be a pussy.
Man, I been clean almost two years.
Man, this one hit ain't
gonna kill you. Come on.
See, we talking about
the '95 Bulls game.
- You scored 58 points.
- That's right.
That ain't all I scored.
Little threeway with two cheerleaders.
You'll always be my hero, man.
That's me. Fucking role model. Come on.
Well, maybe just, just one.
You know that's been up Kenny's ass.
Next is Kareem Said.
Dr. Ferstopnick diagnosed him for
hypertension and prescribed Callen
but his vital signs
have yet to stabilize.
He's not taking his medication.
That doesn't make sense. A guy like
Said has everything to live for.
My guess is that he's concerned about the
effects the drugs could have on his mind.
He doesn't want his judgment clouded.
Well, I can understand that. Oz is the
last place you want to let your guard down.
Can't you switch his prescription?
Yeah, but they all have side effects.
If we don't get him to take something and soon,
it's only a matter of time before
his blood pressure explodes.
Don't think of me as a psychologist.
Don't think of me as a nun.
Think of me as your mother.
Kareem, take your medicine!
Now, Sister, I thought I was in
here for psychiatric evaluation.
You are. Because when you play fast and
loose with high blood pressure, you are crazy.
Said: Oh, Sister, I'm far from crazy.
You see, God endowed me with a mind
and gave me the ability to choose.
I choose to be drug free.
And you make the choice how?
By considering the facts.
The fact is, you will die.
My physical condition is a
small part of a greater reality.
Now, it's been hard. But I am
now at peace with this, Sister.
Now why can't you be?
You, you...
- Asalaam aleikuum, Sister.
You're a good woman. - Yeah.
OK, Huseni Mershaw, this is Kareem Said.
Kareem's gonna help you get used
to the routine in Emerald City.
- Asalaam aleikuum, brother.
- Asalaam aleikuum.
Here, your cuffs.
- Asalaam aleikuum, huh?
- Yeah. Have a nice day.
Prisoner number 97M688, Huseni Mershaw.
Also known as James Monroe Madison.
Convicted August 11, '97. Attemped
murder, assault in the first degree.
Sentence: 20 years. Up for parole in 3.
The Jew shot Omar Selim
because he figured Selim was gonna rip off his
little store. Selim didn't even have a weapon on him.
- And the Jew got off.
- Oh, you know it.
So we had to teach the little
Jew a lesson on respect.
Thank you, brother Huseni. Now we pray.
Imam Said, listen, I think we
gotta do a little more than pray.
We will, brother. Believe me, we will.
Believers are like a single man.
If his eye is affected,
then all of him is affected.
- If the head is affected, then...
- Hey, wanna shut the fuck up?
- ...all of him is affected.
- Yo!
- Got a problem?
- Your bullshit's making me sick.
Don't insult the holy word.
Suck my dick, asshole.
- What's the problem here, guys?
- There ain't no problem, Officer.
Sit down.
I'm sorry if we disturbed you.
Fuck you.
Make nice, Ross. If you can't
handle that, take a walk.
Fuck you too.
Everybody sit down.
He was making fun of the
word of God, Minister.
God does not need you to
defend him from a moron.
What God needs you to do is to
rein in your basic instincts.
What God needs you to do is
be a little patient, brother.
The more of these little
skirmishes you get involved in,
is the more you weaken the
holy war we're about to fight.
- So where you from, Minister?
- From?
Yeah, where you from? You're
not from the ghetto, right?
I was born in the ghetto.
But unlike most, I got out.
I have traveled the world, Huseni,
studied the great religions.
And I have sat at the knee of
mystics, shaman, and madmen.
I know the world, Huseni.
Yeah, well, maybe you been on the mountaintop
so long you forgot where you came from.
I have not forgotten who I am.
Well, maybe Allah sent me to remind you.
Hey, Imam Said's moving
slow, man. It worries me.
He knows best, brother.
Yeah, well, he's blessed by Allah and all
that, but that don't mean he can't be wrong.
So?
So, I'm thinking he might be more valuable
to us as a symbol rather than a leader.
A symbol? What do you mean?
Nothing, man, nothing.
I'm just talking smack.
I'm just wasting time.
Huseni.
What, what? What? What?
Imam, what?
- My heart.
- You're having a heart attack.
Call the doctor.
It is the hand of God.
It is the will of Allah.
Help me, help me!
You must go ahead and die.
All those little aches and pains,
eventually, they add up to something.
Body, mind. Body, mind.
They gotta work together,
or they don't work at all.
You gotta take care of your body.
You gotta take care of your mind.
You gotta love your
body. Most people don't.
Most people hate their bodies.
You gotta get your
mind to love your body.
Even if you're fat around the neck
or even if things don't work
like they're supposed to,
you gotta love your body.
Cause it's all you got to
hold onto. It's all you got.
I'll make a deal with you.
I'll love your body, if you love mine.
Angol script s knai idzts alapjn a feliratot
ksztette s kiegsztette: Ash2000 & Csani