OZ
First Season
- Episode #5 Straight Life
Original Airdate: August 4, 1997
Floods.
You know how you always hear about them people in Iowa or
Missouri or wherever how some big river always overflows?
The fucking water keeps pouring over its riverbanks, out of
control, taking out farms and towns and everything in its path.
Everybody tries to
stop it, but nobody can.
Everybody's lives are wiped out.
Completely destroyed.
And the fucking river,
it don't give a shit.
It just keeps rising.
Year after year after fucked up year.
My question is, are them hicks in
the midwest whacked out or what?
This one joker I seen on TV, his
home had been washed away four times.
Four fucking times.
Why don't he just leave?
Why don't he jump in that pickup
and drive to higher ground?
Or is he like us in Oz?
There ain't no higher ground.
Yeah, what I'm saying is that
your officers are doing a shit job.
The whole concept behind Emerald City is
that you never take your eyes off anyone.
We don't.
Well, then how do you explain Beecher
getting a swastika burned onto his ass
or Miguel Alvarez
cutting his face all up
or inmates using classrooms
to snort fucking heroin?
It's life, Tim. Shit slides through.
If you don't like the way
I run things, replace me.
You know I'm not gonna do that, Diane.
Why? Cause we're fucking each other?
Sorry we're late.
If you ever got here on time, McManus,
I think I'd have a heart attack.
What are we talking about?
Drugs.
My favorite topic.
The more we try and stop the
drugs, the more the drugs get in.
Well, what do you expect?
Outside, they're sentencing
dealers to much longer prison time.
Yeah, we got a prison full of guys who are
experts at moving shit through any system.
Nino Schibetta's got the biggest operation.
We stop him, we make a major dent.
McManus, you wanted Schibetta in Em
City. You said you could reach him.
I will, in time.
Unfortunately, that's one of
the many things we don't have.
I know. When it comes to drugs,
there are two major players involved:
Nino Schibetta and Kareem Said.
Muslims are anti-drugs.
Exactly.
We want your help stopping the flow.
That's your job, not mine.
You know everything about this place. You
could tell us the whens and the wheres.
Yes, and end up dead. No thank you.
I have to take care of
this disease my own way.
Which is?
By fighting the addiction.
Well, you see, that's what I'm trying
to do with my counseling sessions.
You know, you and I have
exact same goals, Kareem,
only because of who we are we can't
help each other acheive these goals.
So more inmates get hurt.
It is so frustrating.
Sister, we both believe
in a greater power.
His will be done.
His will or yours?
Yeah, well, in my experience, God isn't too
helpful unless you give him a little nudge.
What now?
Schibetta's drugs fuck
with people's heads.
It's time I start fucking with his.
The last couple of weeks
have been tough on you, Nino.
Your wife dying,
Dino Ortolani murdered, Joey
D'Angelo out of commission.
Overall, your troops are thinning.
They're getting older, they're more anemic.
Now, the blacks and Latinos are taking
over, on the streets and in here.
So we gotta face it, the
days of the Mafia are over.
Who calls it Mafia?
OK, OK. Let's just say you're at an age,
you outta start to relax a little bit.
Now, I got a friend, DEA.
He says you wanna
talk, he'll make a deal.
A deal?
What's he gonna do, put
me in witness protection?
You are a fool, McManus.
Now, you can try for the next thousand years
not to be a fool, but you'll always be one.
Well, I can't change neither.
I can't turn my back on who I am.
Certainly not for you.
Certainly not for some dumbass DEA deal.
You done with me?
For now.
Attention!
The following inmates are to
be transferred immediately.
As I call your name, gather your belongings
and form a line by Officer Vogelsang.
88P715, Ottovino.
91J224, Jenbro.
85P661, Pellicano.
94R511, Ricatta.
Arrividerci, baby.
Chocolate bars.
Pecans or without?
Both.
You got it.
Graci.
You been handling things pretty good
around here since Joey's accident.
- You do what you gotta do.
- That's right.
The bad blood between you boys and
us, well, with Jefferson Keane cold,
I'm willing to let bygones be gone.
Yeah, me too.
You like tits?
Who doesn't?
My tits are firm and round.
Maybe you could suck my tits.
There are a lot of
brothers who would love to.
If you fuck me over,
I'll cut this hand off.
What the hell was that about?
The future, my brother.
Us owning the future.
Tits. That's what we call drugs.
60% of the violence in
prison is due to tits.
Either people not paying their debts or people
trying to control the traffic. The traffic.
Here in Oz the last few days the
traffic has been bumper to bumper.
Prisoner number 94P442,
Ronald Poklewaldt.
Convicted March 8, '94.
Arson in the second degree.
Sentence: 25 years. Up for parole in 10.
Hey.
Hey, don't touch me.
Oh, so you're hiding behind
the bitch's skirt now, huh?
You hurt me, she'll see you.
I just want my money.
Next week I'm getting a check.
You said that last week.
I know, I know, but I can't be
held responsible for the U.S. mail.
Ow, shit!
Let's go.
- No money, no tits.
- Yeah.
Tomorrow we get healthy.
I want you boys to...
- Who you calling "boys", old man?
- Kenny, shut the fuck up. Take a walk.
- But I'm saying, how you gonna let him just call...?
- Be gone, little nigger.
Look, Nino,
I wanna be there when the shit comes in.
Where's it happen?
Sorry.
It's an old family
recipe. We don't share.
Hey, if we're gonna be partners, yo, we just
outta be up on how big a risk we gotta take.
- Just knowing it works ain't enough?
- No, man.
All right.
So how's it work, Nino?
We know it doesn't go from the
kitchen, otherwise we'd have seen it.
Kitchen's the first place
the cops would look. No,
we use the post office.
Hold this.
A box of socks from my sister. Versace.
It's an old trick.
It still works.
Yeah, but, where do you cut it?
- Here.
- Here?
Here, where?
I ain't telling you everything.
At least not until we've been
in business a little longer.
All right. Cool.
Fuck him.
I don't wanna do no
business with no dago.
- Hey, how's it going?
- Man, we won't be for long.
Schibetta's weak.
He done already lost a lot of his men.
All we got to do is find
out how his operation works,
then we take it over.
- Nino?
- Yeah?
My offer still stands. I wanna be here
for you. I wanna help you any way I can.
OK, kid, thanks.
I said "ok", ok?
OK.
I'll testify against Adebisi,
Markstrom, and Wangler.
We need to figure out
how the drugs get in.
You got any idea how the gangsters are doing it?
- No. No, I don't. I don't.
You find out, you let me know.
Oh, I'll find out all right, and
then I want you to bust Adebisi's ass.
Ronnie,
been to drug counseling recently?
- Sure, sure. I go all the time.
Sister Peter Marie says you
haven't been there for two weeks.
I'll go today. I promise.
Get lost, punk. You aren't squeezing
my tits anymore. You never pay.
No, no, no, that's not why I'm here.
Markstrom and his crew, how
they getting their shit into Oz?
What're you doing? You
doing market research now?
No, man, I'm looking to
fuck those niggers up.
Well, I don't know how they do
it, but I got a couple of guesses.
Sit your ass down.
- Nino, let's talk about this.
- Come on.
You stay out.
It's all right, Kenny. It's all right.
Me and my associates are very
unhappy about this morning's events.
- How did this happen?
- Nino...
My operation's been running
smooth as a silk shirt.
I tell you what's what,
and suddenly the hacks know.
I gotta wonder if one of your boys is the jabber.
- Aw, come on, man, that's impossible.
Anything is possible! You want
to stay in business with me?
Find the leak and plug the leak today.
Don't worry about it. We'll take
care of it, all right? Come on.
Adebisi, stay.
- What's that?
- I don't know, man, but watch him.
Secrets. We all got secrets.
Mostly our secrets are
tied to our addictions,
our obsessions.
You like that bourbon too much?
You get off eating chicks with dicks.
You gotta do it in hiding.
You say you somebody but
you really somebody else.
Only things that matter to
us most, do we keep a secret.
And sometimes, those
secrets will kill you.
Fuck!
Cut him down.
- Markstrom didn't strike me as the suicide type.
- He wasn't.
I'm sorry, Leo.
For what?
- He was your cousin.
- He's not my cousin.
What are you talking about?
That's what you told me when he came in.
That's why you wanted him in Em City.
He's not my cousin. He's
a narc, an undercover cop.
You put an undercover cop in my cell block
and you don't even fucking mention it to me?
Look, I'm trying to put some
brakes on the drug traffic.
I get city Narcotics to send in a man,
I figure the less people that
know about it, the better.
Even so, you shoulda told me, Leo.
And what? Listen to you lecture on prisoners'
rights? About entrapment? No, thanks.
So let me get this straight, Markstrom's
been feeding you info all along?
The idea was to get him
in good with the gangsters,
get him to find out
about their operation.
But somebody gave him up.
Yeah, who?
One of these monkeys in Narcotics
must be talking to the mob.
What? Oh, yes, Governor.
Yes. Yeah, I know. Goodbye.
This time, he wants a lockdown.
Oh, Devlin's fighting
for his political life.
He's trying to take the focus
off him and put it on us.
Yeah, I know. But the bottom
line is, I was gonna do it anyway.
Until we nail whoever's responsible for
Markstrom's murder, I'm locking Oz down, tight.
Man, who woulda thought
Markstrom was a cop?
- Makes you sick, don't it?
- Yeah.
Makes you wonder who
else is under cover.
Could be anybody.
Could be you.
Hey, Nino.
The hacks didn't buy
Markstrom's suicide.
I didn't they think would.
It was more a sign to Glynn.
Don't fuck with us.
Yeah, now they're gonna lock
down this whole fucking place.
For a little while.
And the smuggling
operation, it's busted.
The post office thing?
That's not the way we really do it.
That was just a test to see
what you boys were made of.
The truth is, I'd never
tell you the truth.
The fastest way to end this lockdown
is to pick one of your gang
and have him cop to
the Markstrom hanging.
OK.
I always thought Keane and
Markstrom were holding you back.
From the get-go, you were a guy
that sees how the world gets made.
Adebisi.
Ends in "I".
Sure you're not Italian?
Schibetta ends in "A".
Maybe you African.
Lockdown, gentlemen, lockdown!
Today, Adebisi!
Lockdown, gentlemen, lockdown.
Man, I fucking hate lockdowns.
I mean getting trapped
in this fucking fishbowl,
man, I start fiending
for some fucking tits.
You a tit boy, Groves?
Drugs are bad.
Bullshit.
Man, you had to be fucked
up when you ate your mother.
Mom told me that drugs were bad.
Right. I bet you were a
good little boy, right?
Did everything your mama told you to.
I like your scars.
Now I know why McManus put
us in the same cell together.
You're the only motherfucker in
Em City more fucked up than I am.
Here.
I don't wanna write anybody a fucking
letter. I wanna get fucking high.
- You lick the back.
- Lick the back?
It's liquid LSD.
Groves,
this gives stamp collecting
a whole new meaning, baby.
I don't have to tell you, drugs ain't
the only things to get addicted to.
Some people mainline their
work, some people snort ESPN,
some people needle pop gambling.
There are those that shoot up junk
food, fine wine, cohibas, baby.
Some people get hooked on love.
And like any fiend on the street,
you always need another
bump. Just one more bump, man,
just one more bump.
- Hey.
- Hi.
What's the matter?
Markstrom was murdered.
He was a cop.
I feel responsible.
Diane, Van Harris
confessed to the murder.
Yeah, well, even so. Maybe you're right.
Maybe I am doing a shit job here.
You know what, I got an idea.
Tonight after work you come to my place.
I can't, I gotta drive home.
Mom says Didi's been acting up.
I wanna meet your daughter.
Why don't you bring her into town,
three of us will go to dinner?
And then what'll I do with her?
This isn't exactly a take your
daughter to work kind of place.
I love you, Diane.
Do you?
No, you're supposed to
say, "I love you too, Tim."
The night of Keane's
execution, you know,
what we did, it was really fucked up.
And I don't know why.
Was it loneliness?
Why does the why matter?
Well, it doesn't, does it?
I came up here to get the
file on the new arrival.
His name is Scott Ross.
Scott Ross?
- Oh, shit.
- Is there a problem?
Nah, it's nothing I can't handle.
Prisoner number 97R518, Scott Ross.
Convicted June 4, '97.
Possession of marijuana
with intent to distribute.
Third conviction. Sentence:
Life without parole.
Three strikes, sucker!
- Wait here.
- Sure.
Since when you been working Oz?
About six months.
This is great.
No, no it's not.
Always dreamed of you
having me in cuffs.
Look, just because we knew each other in a former
life, doesn't mean you're getting any special treatment.
I love it when you play tough.
I'm not playing, Scott. Mack?
Mark Mack, Scott Ross.
Mack is your sponsor. He'll help
you get acquainted with the rules.
Take him to Em City.
You knew her on the outside?
Yeah. Me and her ex
used to ride together.
In there. Top bunk, all right?
All right, gentlemen,
the lockdown is over.
Hey.
I'm gonna give you ten minutes
to get your hands off my dick.
- Schillinger, you fuck.
- Scotty, how long you in for?
Life.
Oh, man.
What?
You got any cigarettes?
No smoking. Put the butt out.
Diane, I'm not asking
for any special favors but
we've known each other for a long time.
Have we?
I was married to Glen
for four fun filled years.
During that time, you were
finishing up a six year sentence.
We were on the road
together maybe five months.
They were a great five months.
All you did was come on to me.
If Glen hadn't been so fucked
up on coke, he'd have noticed.
I was a man in love. I still am.
Oh, please. Save it for the shower room.
Diane, I know what
your life is like now,
raising a kid on your own,
working midnights shifts.
I hear you're doing double
shifts cause you need the money.
I got a way to make you money.
You looking out for
my best interests, huh?
Yeah.
Like I said, save it.
Get your ass back to Em City.
Next item, overtime.
The good news is, based on the successful conclusion
of negotiations between the Department of Corrections
and the Officers' Union,
we have a contract.
The bad news is, because the
overtime rate is now so high,
the Commissioner has decided to no longer
allow officers to work double shifts.
What? This sucks!
The department gave in
to the union's demands,
knowing they never intended
to pay any overtime?
That's how deals get made.
Hey, what're you
complaining about, lady Di?
Frees you up to spend more
time with your boyfriend.
What are you talking about?
Yeah, Healy, what're you trying to say?
You two wanna pretend you're
not fucking each other, fine.
You're a funny guy, you know that?
Knock it off, you two!
McManus! McManus, sit down!
- You fucking prick.
- Sit down!
Healy, keep your comments to yourself.
Next item.
Fuck them.
No, Timmy, it's not that easy.
Like it or not, we
work with these people.
If they don't respect us, it
makes the day ten times harder.
Are you saying we can't
see each other anymore?
Look, this job is all I
have. Do you understand that?
You have a college education,
a big time reputation.
If I lose this, it's back to
cleaning other people's houses.
It's welfare.
I have a daughter to feed
and a mother getting old.
I can give you money.
You have alimony and a mortgage,
you can't afford to take me
on. And I wouldn't want you to.
- I know.
- No, I'll see you, Tim.
We both know cigarettes
is money in the joint.
Want someone to do your
laundry, a couple of sticks.
Want someone to get
rolled, a carton or two,
depending on who it is.
Problem is, they got a
really short shelf life.
You can't hold 'em,
you gotta keep moving.
Supply and demand, baby,
that's what I'm talking about.
I bring 'em in, you sell 'em.
Carton a day, that's it.
Come on, what do you say?
OK.
Put the cigarette out.
That's my baby.
Not all drugs are recreational.
Some are benign or,
supposedly benign.
I got the final results back from your
tests. You're suffering from hypertension.
The curse of my people.
African Americans are genetically
predisposed to the condition.
No, Doctor, it's not genetics.
High blood pressure is caused by racism.
There are some studies out suggesting a link
between racial discrimination and hypertension,
but the data is inconclusive.
Well, it may be inconclusive
to the scientists,
but I know that it's a fact.
Men of color in the working class have
a higher blood pressure than whites,
or even black professionals. Why?
Because we are forced to
accept unfair treatment, Doctor.
I'm not really interested in the
politics, Said, I care about your health.
And if we don't do something, you're
headed for heart disease, stroke,
damage to the other organs. So
I'm going to prescribe Zoltanolin.
What are the side effects?
Low heartbeat,
lightheadedness if you
stand up too quickly.
That's won't do.
Daily I kneel and I pray to Mecca.
What else do you have?
Callum. Constipation, nausea, dizziness.
No. My mind must function clearly.
All drugs have side effects.
Well, perhaps that's God's way of
telling us we shouldn't be taking them.
Either you taking
something, or you'll die.
Believe me, Doctor, I
have no intention of dying.
Can I go now?
Sure.
I'm sorry that you're ill.
And who told you that I was ill?
God.
Oh, yes. You talk to God.
When he's in town.
Well, in Islam, we believe that only
two people spoke to God directly.
Mohammad, and praise
be to him, and Moses.
So, you see, you are
in excellent company.
You think I'm lying or deluded.
Oh, yeah.
I may well be.
I do know sometimes I can
see inside men's souls.
And can you see into mine, old man?
Yes.
And what is there?
Anger.
Yes, I am angry.
I am angry at a society that cripples
my people and infects their bodies.
No, you're angry at God.
I am not.
My illness is Allah's will
and I accept the bad as well
as the good that God gives me.
Still, you're angry at him and afraid.
Afraid of dying.
That is not true.
You watched Jefferson
Keane die, die gladly.
Keane embraced death like a
lover, like a traveler going home.
You saw that and you were afraid.
You realized you
aren't as willing to go.
Get out of here, old man.
Go.
The ever-increasing scandal surrounding Governor James
Devlin accepting kickbacks took another bizarre turn today,
when his wife Evangeline Devlin
moved out of the Governor's mansion.
Though no official word has been
given, sources say that Mrs. Devlin
has learned of an affair
between the Governor and...
The doctor told me what's going on.
That is not your concern, McManus.
He told me you won't
take your medication.
I haven't decided anything as yet.
Well, you don't have a
choice. Take the drugs.
And what if I refuse?
- I'll force you to.
- How?
We'll open up your mouth and I'll
stuff the pills down your throat myself.
OK, let's make that deal, McManus.
Give me what I want.
I can't tell you much about
how the drugs get into Oz,
except to say look at your own house.
What's that mean?
- That's a pretty big accusation.
- Not really.
There are plenty of examples of
officers smuggling drugs into prisons.
Solidad, Attica, here in Oz in '82.
I remember. I was working solitary.
- Two of my best friends got busted.
- So, then?
- I'll start an investigation.
- Good.
Of the entire staff. Everyone from
the officers to the librarian to you.
I'll take it slow, because if it's true,
I don't wanna spook them.
I want to make the charges stick.
Hey, Roger.
Hey, morning, Mike.
- See the Toronto game?
- Yeah, Gaston's a spaz.
- How much'd you lose?
- Don't ask.
Hey, Diane. You heading out?
Yep.
This graveyard shift's a killer.
- O'Reily.
- Yeah?
Go see Schibetta.
Since when are you his Western Union?
Since we partners.
- We?
- Yeah.
You're the monkey chained
to his organ grinder.
Better watch that pretty little ass.
No need. You're too
busy watching it for me.
And keep your fucking hands off me.
Oh, I'm scared of you.
You wanted to see me, Nino?
Yeah, come on in.
No, thanks. I've never
been big on tomatoes.
You Irish. You got no appreciation
for the simple things in life.
What's simpler than a potato?
Sit.
You been saying if I need it,
you'd be willing to help out.
Anything.
You know Adebisi's gonna shank
you the first chance he gets.
Don't worry about Adebisi.
He's a mongrel, but effective.
From you I need a more
sophisticated favor.
I need to close down
Healy's drug operation.
Healy? Officer Healy?
Don't say you know nothing about it.
Your brother and Healy are friends.
Healy's been your archangel
since you got to Oz.
You been running tits for him.
You know, I don't know what you're...
I don't hold it against
you. I'd have done the same.
Only, Healy's business is
starting to cut into mine
and that I can't have happen.
So I am looking to you for assistance.
You want me to set him up?
Yeah. If you do, I promise I'll
take care of you. What do you say?
You've been good to me.
Is that your answer?
I'll do it.
- Bueni.
- So what's the plan?
The plan is up to you. I
don't care about the hows.
Just get it done.
All right.
- I need more tits.
- Oh, yeah?
I gave you a huge pair
a couple of days ago.
What can I say? We
go braless in Em City.
When can you get us some more?
Later.
- Yo, you looking for me?
- Yeah.
How'd you like some tits for free?
I don't kill.
You don't have to kill.
What do you want to do?
Go see your pals upstairs.
And tell 'em what?
Tell 'em that you found
another drug connection.
- Well, who you gonna bust this time?
- Me.
McManus! Get him out of here!
That's going on your record.
Big fucking deal.
I gave this place everything I had.
And then you decided to
take everything you could.
Look, I know working
here is no paradise,
but you swore an oath
and you broke that oath!
I got no sympathy for you.
Get him away from me.
You wait, Warden. You
wait 'til you need somebody
to back you up and I won't be here.
Then you can kiss your ass goodbye!
Will you testify against Healy?
No.
I jabber on him, every other hack will be
waiting in line to take a whack at me too.
Fine. Officer Hunt?
See you in a month, O'Reily.
Hey, O'Reily, any idea
who ratted on Healy?
Beats the shit outta me.
But if I were a betting man,
I'd put my money on Poklewaldt.
Patient's name is Ronald Poklewaldt.
It's severe head trauma.
How are the vital signs?
Let me out of here!
You're done.
Piece of cake.
Look, what is this fucking
pinocchio? I don't play games.
How do you keep that
hat on your head, velcro?
- Deal me in.
- Play Pinochle?
No, I can learn.
Adebisi, I'll see you later.
OK, each player gets four cards.
One card, face up, that's the...
You're in a mood.
I'm in a mood, all right.
I'm in a mood to kill.
Anybody in particular?
The mick and dago.
Yeah, well, I can go for a
piece of Schibetta's ass myself.
Yeah, well, stick around, little brother.
When the time is right, he's all yours.
He's all mine.
You take a drug, right. The
chemicals, they rush through your body,
rush through your brain.
And the sensations,
you want the sensations
again and again and again.
But let me tell you, you can also get
addicted to grief, to guilt, to hate.
Cause when you feel dead inside,
even bad sensations make
you feel like you're alive.
What, that's it? No good night kiss?
I'm beginning to think
you don't love my anymore.
I do.
Say it. Say you love me.
I love you.
No, you see, you said it
but you didn't mean it.
I do mean it, sir.
No, I'm telling you, the romance
has gone out of our relationship.
But, I have a cure.
I was saving this for your birthday,
but I think we need it now.
No, thanks.
Come on, you're gonna hurt my feelings.
You know what happens
when you hurt my feelings.
Put some on.
No.
OK. Hey, I understand.
You wanna surprise me.
Gonna wait for a special occasion
to get yourself all prettied up.
That is so sweet.
Hey, I can wait. Not too long.
What? A nun can't look beautiful?
Tobias, are you all right?
Sure.
You think I'm blind?
I'm a drug counselor,
for God's sake. If I can't spot the
signs, I might as well tear up my license.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Listen, I know how
hideous life is in Oz,
especially for a man like you with no streets skills,
no preparation for the reality of it all but, Tobias,
Tobias,
drugs are not the answer.
They only make the
questions more difficult.
I want you to start coming
to counseling sessions.
Whatever.
I'm not sure when he started
but my sense is not too long ago.
I'm hoping that we can
nip this in the bud.
Well, I'll have the officers on
duty monitor Beecher carefully
and see who he's hanging out with.
Well, it can't be
Schillinger who's supplying.
He's so antidrug,
he makes me look like Robert Downey Jr.
Maybe we should also talk
to members of his family.
Well, his wife took
the kids and moved away,
but he does have parents and siblings.
What about an intervention?
I think that's too much, too soon.
But why don't we invite one of his
relatives to visit him and see what happens?
You know, on the outside, Beecher
had a history of alcohol abuse.
Oh, I know. How pathetic is that?
The man gets jailed for one addiction
and we watch him get hooked on another.
You smell good, Mother.
The same old Chanel, I'm afraid.
I remember you and Dad
getting ready to go out,
him putting on his tux,
you wearing the latest gown,
and that scent wafting through the air.
But that was a long time ago
in a galaxy far, far away.
Toby, I had a conversation with the
man who runs the place where you live.
McManus?
He told me that he
suspects you of using drugs.
- Mother...
- Tell me.
Mother, you don't know
what it's like in here.
- I can imagine.
- No, you can't!
And I thank God every night for that.
So if you wanna tell me how
Agnes is doing in law school
or Dad's most recent fishing trip
or Grandma's Winnebago, fine.
But if you came here to lecture me,
tell me to just say no, don't.
Don't put that final knife in my heart.
Toby...
Hello, Tobias. Come on in.
Sit down.
OK, we've got a new member
to our group, Tobias Beecher.
I think you know Augustus
and Ron from Em City
and that's John and
Bill and Whitney Munson.
Beecher. I know a Beecher. Cyrus.
- Are you any relation?
- No.
Good. Man was a cocksucker.
OK. The idea here is for
us in a small group to talk
about ourselves, our
feelings, our addictions,
in the hope that we can find the cause.
I know the cause.
I like the shit.
All right, that's fine. Pleasure
plays a very strong factor.
Underneath, maybe
there's something else.
There's a deeper need, a hunger,
an emptiness that has to be filled.
So, Tobias, why don't you tell
us what you're addicted to?
You know. They know.
Yeah, ok. Augustus, you wanna
talk about your addiction?
I was a crack addict. Been
squeaky clean 22 months.
Yes. Ron?
Speed's my bag.
How long you been clean?
A year.
Whitney?
I quit seven times over the last 52
years. This'll be my longest period,
five years, three months, and six days.
What are you addicted to?
- Since I been inside?
- Yeah.
Anything I can get my hands
on, but originally opium.
I had been decorated with the
Purple Heart for valor. Valor.
Only I knew I was really a fraud.
Even after I was discharged I
couldn't take the uniform off.
During the war, off in the
Orient, I got hooked into opium.
My true self lay in that
quixotic little grunt.
Prisoner number 45M242, Whitney Munson.
Convicted March 2, '45.
Murder in the first degree, criminal possession of a
controlled substance. Sentence: 110 years. Up for parole in 60.
Question, why'd you strangle the whore?
I didn't think I was.
I thought I was being affectionate.
Her neck was so pale, so thin, so fine.
And you've been in prison
for 52 years, right?
That's right.
I've only got eight years
left until my parole.
Come the year 2005, I'm out of here.
Look, I can't stay here anymore and listen
to any more of these fucking stories!
Tobias. Sit down.
- No, it's not helping!
- Sit down!
It's not helping!
Hello.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm here to give you a makeover.
Huh?
Your boyfriend told me to.
He said don't take no for an answer.
My God,
you're even prettier
than I thought you'd be.
Here it is a beautiful baby.
Miguel, your baby's dead.
Te quiero. Te quiero mucho.
I ain't saying drugs are good.
But when your past is
past and your present sucks
and your future holds nothing but
broken promises and dead dreams,
the drugs'll kill the pain.
Listen up, America.
You ain't ever gonna get rid
of drugs until you cure pain.
Angol script s knai idzts alapjn a
feliratot ksztette s kiegsztette: Ash2000