>> SO WE'VE BEEN CALLED OUT
TO HIS HIKING TRAIL
BECAUSE THERE'S SOME REPORTS
THAT SOME TEENAGERS
ARE DIGGING BAGS OF DOG POOP
OUT OF THE TRASH
AND HAVING DOG POOP FIGHTS.
>> I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
OH, MY GOD, IT'S REAL.
>> UH, YEAH, I'M NOT GONNA--
I'M NOT GONNA GO DEAL WITH THIS.
I'M LEAVING.
>> HEY.
HEY.
HELLO?
BOYS.
I AM LESLIE KNOPE.
I WORK FOR THE DEPARTMENT
OF PARKS AND RECREATION.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
COOL IT.
OKAY.
NO!
AHH!
THAT'S DISGUSTING.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NO! OH!
HELP! HELP!
TOM!
AHH!
NO!
OH, IT SMELLS SO BAD.
OH! OH!
WHAT WOULD YOU THINK
THIS WAS FUN? OW!
OH, REALLY?
OH, HEY, HEY.
YOU LIKE IT?
BOOM.
[groaning]
OKAY.
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
WHO WANTS IT?
HA, HA.
WHOO, MISSED IT.
YEAH, OH!
[panting]
ACTUALLY, THIS IS A LITTLE FUN.
THIS IS FUN.
OH.
[triumphant music]
*
OH, HEY, TOM,
CHECK IT OUT.
NORTON CONSTRUCTION
JUST SENT THIS OVER.
>> WHOA, MAMA.
>> I LOVE GREAT LAKES WINE.
>> YOU CAN HAVE THE WINE.
I WANNA TAKE THAT CHEESE
AND DO TERRIBLE THINGS TO IT.
>> OH, DAH, DAH, DAH.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU KNOW AS WELL AS I DO
THAT WE ARE NOT ALLOWED
TO ACCEPT GIFTS OVER $25
FOR CORRUPTION REASONS.
WE LIVE IN A FISH BOWL, AND
THE PUBLIC IS ALWAYS WATCHING.
THAT'S WHY I GO
TWO TOWNS OVER
IF I WANT TO RENT A MOVIE
WITH NUDITY IN IT.
>> MMM.
>> YEAH, I PROBABLY
SHOULDN'T HAVE SAID THAT.
BUT YOU CANNOT
ENJOY THIS BASKET.
I'M SO SORRY.
SO TO AVOID TEMPTATION
I'M GONNA LOCK IT UP.
>> WHEN YOU'RE
IN THE GOVERNMENT,
THERE'S A MILLION WAYS
TO EXPLOIT YOUR POWER.
HAVE I EVER GIVEN IN
TO THAT TEMPTATION?
NO, NEVER.
I'M NOT THAT KIND
OF POLITICIAN.
OFFICIAL PARKS AND REC
BUSINESS.
I JUST NEED TO GRAB
A QUICK HOT DOG.
SORRY ABOUT THAT,
LITTLE GIRL.
YOU CAN HAVE THE NEXT ONE.
I HAVE A MORAL CODE,
AND I NEVER VIOLATE IT.
PEOPLE LOOK AT ME
AND THEY SAY,
"WOW, TOM,
YOU ARE SO PURE.
"YOU'RE LIKE A BROWN SUPERMAN
WITH A BEARD
"THAT JUST STANDS
FOR JUSTICE AND TRUTH
AND THE AMERICAN WAY."
>> SO, ANN,
I ASKED APRIL TO CREATE
ONE OF THOSE SOCIAL NETWORK
INTERNET PROFILES
FOR THE SULLIVAN STREET PIT.
SO ARE YOU GUYS READY
FOR THE DEBUT?
>> YES, CAN WE CUT
THAT RED RIBBON
AROUND YOUR MONITOR NOW?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I LOVE A GOOD RIBBON CUTTING.
WOW.
OH, APRIL, THAT'S GOOD.
KIDS.
>> HEY, LOOK, THE PIT
ALREADY HAS SIX FRIENDS.
>> OH, YEAH, MARK.
MARK'S A FRIEND.
>> WHOA, WHOA, YOU GUYS
GOTTA SEE MARK'S PROFILE.
LOOK AT THE PHOTOS
OF THESE LADIES ON HIS PAGE.
>> WOW.
>> SICK.
>> MAYBE THOSE
ARE HIS RELATIVES.
>> YEAH, MAYBE FAKE BOOBS
RUN IN HIS FAMILY.
>> LOOK AT THIS LADY.
SHE'S GOT A THONG ON HER FACE.
>> OH, MY GOD, HIS FAVORITE
MOVIE IS DANCES WITH WOLVES.
>> OKAY, WE'RE GOOD.
WE'LL KEEP
CHECKING IN ON THIS.
>> WHERE IS MARK ANYWAY?
>> ATTENDING
YET ANOTHER MEETING
OF THE OLD BOYS' CLUB.
POLITICS IS FULL
OF BOYS' CLUBS,
FORMAL AND INFORMAL.
BEHIND ME ARE ALL THE MEMBERS
OF THE CITY COUNCIL
OVER THE PAST 30 YEARS.
AND EVERY DAY,
AS A WOMAN,
I HAVE TO WALK PAST
THIS WALL OF MEN.
IT CAN BE VERY UPSETTING,
ESPECIALLY BECAUSE
OF THAT GUY.
NO MATTER
WHAT DIRECTION I MOVE,
HE'S ALWAYS STARING
AT MY CHEST.
HMM?
SEE?
>> WHAT ARE THEY DOING
OUT THERE?
>> WHEELING AND DEALING.
DIVVYING UP THE EMPIRE.
>> EH, MY WIFE
GOT ME THIS SHIRT.
SHE SWEARS IT MAKES ME
LOOK THINNER.
>> IT KINDA DOES.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT WE SHOULD DO?
LET'S GO OUT THERE.
LET'S BUST UP
THAT OLD BOYS' CLUB.
WE'RE DOING GREAT WORK
IN THE GOVERNMENT.
WE DESERVE TO BE INCLUDED.
>> SURE, YEAH,
I COULD USE A BEER.
>> YES, ANN, THAT'S GOOD.
THINK LIKE A MAN.
APRIL, WE'RE LEAVING.
YOU'RE IN CHARGE,
AND IT'S BECAUSE YOU'RE A WOMAN.
>> WHAT, DO YOU REALLY LIKE
RED TAPE AND UPHILL BATTLES?
>> HEY, LESLIE.
>> HEY.
>> WHAT IS UP?
>> I'LL TELL YOU WHAT'S UP.
COUPLE OF LADIES ARE COMING TO
BUST UP YOUR LITTLE BOYS' CLUB.
>> AWESOME.
GLAD TO HAVE YOU.
GET YOU A BEER.
>> [whispered]
WE'RE IN.
>> HEY, I'M BRIAN.
>> HI, BRIAN.
LESLIE KNOPE,
DEPUTY DIRECTOR OF--
>> DRINK THAT.
>> OKAY.
>> I'M ANN, EVERYONE.
I DON'T WORK HERE.
>> ANN.
>> SO WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
TALKING ABOUT?
WHAT'S TOPIC DU JOUR?
OH, OH, OH.
[bottles shattering]
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
THAT WAS THE SOUND
OF A GLASS CEILING
BEING SHATTERED.
THE BOYS' CLUB IS MORE ABOUT
SOCIALIZING THAN WORK, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, YOU GOTTA LOOSEN UP.
I KINDA FEEL LIKE
I'M ALREADY IN THE BOYS' CLUB.
I MEAN, LOOK AT THOSE BITCHES
CLEAN UP AFTER ME.
>> SO IS THIS, LIKE, YOUR
REGULAR TUESDAY NIGHT SCENE?
>> WELL, IT'S JUST
A WAY TO UNWIND, YOU KNOW?
>> REALLY DIFFERENT FROM
YOUR FRIDAY NIGHT CROWD, RIGHT?
>> WHAT CROWD?
>> YOU KNOW, THE GIRLS WITH
THE TRIBAL BACK TATTOOS
WHO DRINK RED BULL
FOR A LIVING.
>> OH.
>> THAT CROWD.
>> OH, I LIKE THIS.
THIS IS BANTER.
BANTER'S FUN.
>> WHERE'D THAT COME FROM?
>> WE WERE JUST ON THE COMPUTER
LOOKING AT YOUR PROFILE.
YOU KNOW, YOU HAVE A FRIEND
WHO HAS A TATTOO
THAT SAYS "DADDY'S GIRL"
AND BOTH WORDS ARE MISSPELLED.
>> OH, MIXING IT UP
WITH THE BOYS.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA SAY?
WHAT'S YOUR COMEBACK?
>> THOSE AREN'T REALLY
MY FRIENDS ANYMORE.
I DON'T HANG OUT WITH THEM.
>> OH, BOO.
BRENDANAWICZ,
THAT'S SOME WEAK SAUCE.
YOU NEED TO HIT HARDER.
>> NATALIE,
IT'S YOUR SISTER.
PICK ME UP OR I'M GONNA DRAW
ALL OVER YOUR JEANS.
>> WELL, IT'S OFFICIAL,
PEOPLE.
WE'RE OUTTA BEER.
>> AHH, THAT'S THE CUE.
SEE YOU LATER, LESLIE.
IT WAS NICE HANGING OUT,
YOU KNOW, AFTER WORK HOURS.
>> WAIT.
>> I THINK I'M GONNA
TAKE OFF TOO.
>> YEAH, I SHOULD GO, LESLIE.
>> WAIT, YOU GUYS, LET'S KEEP
THIS GOOD FEELING GOING.
IT'S JUST GETTING STARTED.
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE PARTIES
USUALLY GET STARTED
WHEN YOU RUN OUT OF BOOZE.
>> OKAY, WAIT.
JUST HOLD ON A SECOND.
I GOT WINE.
>> all: HEY!
>> AND CHEESE.
>> WHOO.
>> GOOD MORNING.
LAST NIGHT IN A FOOLISH ATTEMPT
TO INFILTRATE A BOYS' CLUB
I VIOLATED THE GOVERNMENT
EMPLOYEE ETHICS CODE
OF THE STATE OF INDIANA.
I HAVE ALWAYS TRIED TO LIVE
MY LIFE IN AN ETHICAL WAY,
AND LAST NIGHT I FAILED.
I REALIZE I HAVE LET DOWN
EVERY FEMALE
PUBLIC OFFICIAL IN AMERICA,
AND I WOULD LIKE TO APOLOGIZE
TO THEM RIGHT NOW,
INDIVIDUALLY
AND IN ALPHABETICAL ORDER.
MICHELE BACHMANN,
REPUBLICAN, MINNESOTA,
I AM SORRY.
TAMMY BALDWIN,
DEMOCRAT, WISCONSIN,
I'M SO SORRY, TAMMY.
MELISSA BEAN.
[dog growling]
[video game sounds]
>> OKAY.
DOUBLE SHIFT, REMEMBER?
SO I WON'T SEE
YOU TILL TOMORROW.
ARE YOU GONNA BE OKAY?
>> OH, YEAH.
I GOT, UH...DINNER.
>> OH, GOD.
HONEY, CAN YOU JUST
CLEAN UP A LITTLE BIT?
>> I'LL TRY.
DON'T EXPECT MUCH.
>> OKAY, WELL,
I'LL DO IT WHEN I GET HOME.
>> YOU WILL?
>> YES.
>> ANN IS AMAZING.
SHE TAKES CARE OF ME.
SHE TAKES CARE OF SICK PEOPLE,
SICK BABIES.
SHE IS AN ANGEL.
AND I SERIOUSLY LOVE HER.
HARD.
SHE'S GOING TO BE GONE
FOR THE NEXT 24 HOURS.
SO I MADE THIS LIST,
AND BASICALLY
THIS PLACE IS GONNA BE
LIKE A SPARKLING PALACE
WHEN SHE RETURNS.
I TOOK A BUNCH
OF PAIN KILLERS.
THEY'RE ABOUT TO KICK IN,
SO I'M READY TO GO.
>> HERE IT IS.
LET'S CLEAR THE AIR.
LAST NIGHT I OPENED UP
THIS GIFT BASKET
FOR MY OWN PLEASURE.
>> REALLY?
LESLIE KNOPE, USUALLY SUCH
A PRUDISH STICKLER
FOR THE RULES.
>> I'M NOT HAPPY
ABOUT IT EITHER, TOM.
>> IT'S LIKE I DON'T EVEN
KNOW YOU ANYMORE.
>> LAST YEAR YOU WROTE ME UP
FOR MAKING PERSONAL PHONE CALLS
TO MY MOM.
>> YES, I DID,
AND I WOULD DO IT AGAIN.
TWO WRONGS
DO NOT MAKE A RIGHT.
>> YES, BUT SHE
WAS IN THE HOSPITAL.
>> I DID NOT KNOW THAT
AT THE TIME.
>> SO CAN I HAVE THE BASKET?
>> NO, I'M SORRY.
IT'S EVIDENCE.
>> IT'S A NICE BASKET.
>> WHAT WOULD YOU
PUT IN THERE?
>> I DON'T KNOW,
POTPOURRI.
>> THAT'S A LOT OF POTPOURRI.
>> HEY, I AM NOT THE ONE
ON TRIAL HERE.
>> I APPRECIATE
AND THANK YOU IN ADVANCE
FOR YOUR UNWAVERING SUPPORT.
>> I THINK YOU SHOULD
GO TO JAIL,
THINK ABOUT WHAT YOU'VE DONE.
>> GO TO JAIL?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> RON,
I HAVE A VERY IMPORTANT
AND VERY LONG STORY
TO TELL YOU.
>> PUT IT IN AN EMAIL?
>> NOPE.
IT HAPPENED RIGHT OUT THERE,
RIGHT OUTSIDE THIS WINDOW.
WHY CAN'T I LOOK AWAY?
>> LET'S NOT BLOW THIS
OUT OF PROPORTION.
>> I WILL BLOW THIS
IN PROPORTION.
THE MINIMUM PUNISHMENT FOR THIS
IS AN OFFICIAL REPRIMAND
FROM THE CITY MANAGER.
>> IT'S NOT THAT BIG A DEAL.
>> MAYBE IN YOUR WORLD
IT ISN'T A BIG DEAL.
YOU'RE A WHITE PROTESTANT MAN
WITH A FULL, RICH MOUSTACHE.
BUT I AM A WOMAN,
AND I NEED TO HOLD MYSELF UP
TO A HIGHER STANDARD.
>> THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
YOU'RE PUNISHING YOURSELF
MORE THAN ANYBODY ELSE
IS GONNA PUNISH YOU.
>> NO.
WHAT DO YOU SUGGEST WE DO?
YOU THINK WE SHOULD
COVER THIS UP?
>> NO, I'M NOT SAYING THAT.
NO ONE SAID "COVER-UP".
>> GOOD BECAUSE THE COVER-UP
IS WORSE THAN THE CRIME.
WHEN YOU SPILL SOMETHING
AND YOU TRY TO WIPE IT UP
WITH SOMETHING THAT'S DIRTY,
THEN YOU GET DOUBLE DIRTY.
>> PLEASE DON'T
MAKE THIS WORSE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
GOOD AFTERNOON.
SINCE WE LAST SPOKE,
I HAVE TAKEN EXTRAORDINARY STEPS
TO MAKE FURTHER AMENDS
FOR THE MISTAKES THAT I'VE MADE.
I HAVE WRITTEN
A FULL CONFESSION,
WHICH I WILL BE EMAILING
TO EVERYONE IN THE ENTIRE
PAWNEE GOVERNMENT.
I'VE ALSO ATTACHED A LINK
TO THE PIT'S WEB PAGE
JUST TO REMIND PEOPLE
OF ALL THE GOOD WORK THAT I DO.
I ASKED RON TO BLOW
THE WHISTLE ON ME,
AND HE REFUSED.
AND THAT IS WHY
I HAD TO WHISTLE-BLOW MYSELF.
>> I WISH I COULD SAY
SOME OF THIS MESS WAS ANN'S,
BUT IT'S ALL MINE.
I'M KIND OF A NESTER.
EH, NOT BAD FOR A GUY
WITH TWO BROKEN LEGS.
HEY.
>> DOING A LITTLE
EXPERIMENT TONIGHT
TO SEE WHAT WILL
GET ME DRUNKER--
DRINKING WINE--
>> LESLIE, COME HERE.
SEE WHAT APRIL
PUT ON THE PIT'S WEB PAGE.
>> RIGHT NOW DRINKING WINE
IS WINNING.
>> OH, MY GOD,
WHAT AM I LOOKING AT?
>> A VIDEO OF ME DRINKING
SOME OF THAT WINE YOU STOLE.
>> WHAT?
WHY DID YOU DO THIS?
>> BECAUSE I WAS WAITING
FOR MY SISTER AND I WAS BORED,
AND MY HAIR
LOOKED REALLY GOOD.
>> AND YOU PUT IT
IN THE PIT'S WEB PAGE?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY, TAKE THIS OFF.
OKAY, I JUST SENT AN EMAIL
TO EVERYONE IN THE GOVERNMENT
AND I PUT A LINK
TO THIS PAGE.
>> [humming]
>> A YOUNG LAWBREAKER.
A FUTURE LESLIE KNOPE.
PLAY IT AGAIN FOR US, JERRY.
>> YOU GOT IT.
>> LESLIE.
SHE'S 19 YEARS OLD.
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
NOT TO MAKE THIS WORSE.
>> AND I HEARD YOU
LOUD AND CLEAR.
>> BUT THEN YOU MADE IT WORSE.
THE DISCIPLINARY COMMITTEE'S
HAVING A HEARING TOMORROW
AND YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE TO TESTIFY.
>> OH, NO.
>> APRIL MIGHT GET DISMISSED.
YOU COULD GET FIRED.
>> OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, NO.
OH, GOD.
OH, THIS BENCH
IS SO UNCOMFORTABLE.
OW, HELP.
PLEASE, RON.
RON, RON,
TELL ME IT'S GONNA BE OKAY.
>> IT'S GONNA--
>> RON, WHERE ARE YOU?
>> IT'LL--HANG IN.
>> RON.
>> OKAY, YOU'RE OKAY.
>> [sobbing]
GOOD EVENING.
I'VE SPOKEN TO YOU
A COUPLE TIMES
ABOUT SOMETHING
THAT HAPPENED,
BUT I DON'T WANNA--
I DON'T WANNA
TALK ABOUT IT ANYMORE.
>> SO THE DISCIPLINARY
COMMITTEE AWAITS.
FEELING GOOD?
FEELING STRONG?
>> NOT REALLY, NO.
>> DO YOU WANT ME TO RUN
SOME TEST QUESTIONS WITH YOU,
MAYBE GIVE YOU AN IDEA
OF WHAT THE DISCIPLINARY
COMMITTEE WILL BE LIKE?
>> YEAH, THAT'D BE GREAT.
YEAH, THANKS, TOM.
>> OKAY.
SO, MS. KNOPE,
YOU'RE ACCUSED
OF STEALING WINE.
HOW MANY DRINKS DO YOU HAVE
PER WEEK ON AVERAGE?
>> ZERO.
ZERO TO SIX.
>> I'M GONNA WRITE DOWN "TEN".
>> YEAH.
>> DO YOU EVER CHEAT
ON YOUR TAXES?
>> NO, NO, NO, NEVER.
>> GOOD.
YOU'RE DOING GREAT.
HOW MANY SEXUAL PARTNERS
HAVE YOU HAD IN THE LAST YEAR?
>> ARE THEY GONNA ASK THAT?
>> THIS IS A DEPOSITION-STYLE
HEARING, MS. KNOPE.
NOTHING IS OFF-LIMITS.
YOU HAVE TO ANSWER.
NOW HOW MANY SEXUAL PARTNERS
HAVE YOU HAD IN THE LAST YEAR?
>> ZERO TO SIX.
>> ZERO.
HAVE YOU EVER THOUGHT
ABOUT RON SEXUALLY?
>> WHAT?!
>> INCLUDING DREAMS.
HAVE YOU EVER HAD
A SEXUAL DREAM
ABOUT OUR BOSS,
RON SWANSON?
>> NO, ABSOLUTELY NOT, NO.
>> YES.
>> NO.
>> NOW IN THIS RECURRING DREAM
THAT YOU HAVE ABOUT RON,
IS HE, LIKE, A REGULAR RON
OR IS HE HALF-RON, HALF-ANIMAL,
LIKE A CENTAUR?
>> WHAT?
>> IS HE WEARING
A FOOTBALL UNIFORM?
ARE YOU MAKING LOVE TO HIM
ON A COUCH
SHAPED LIKE HIS MOUSTACHE?
IS HE COVERED IN POWERADE?
>> NO, OKAY,
TIME-OUT, TIME-OUT.
>> THIS COMMITTEE DOESN'T
TAKE TIME-OUTS, MS. KNOPE.
NOW ANSWER THE QUESTION.
>> I NEED SOMETHING TO DRINK.
>> HOW 'BOUT SOME STOLEN WINE?
>> NO, I MEANT WATER.
>> THANK YOU FOR YOUR TIME,
MS. KNOPE.
YOU'RE FIRED.
SO THAT'S KINDA YOUR
WORST-CASE SCENARIO, YOU KNOW?
IF YOU CAN HANDLE THAT,
I THINK YOU'LL BE FINE.
>> GREAT.
RON, THANK YOU FOR BEING
HERE WITH ME TODAY.
>> I'M YOUR DEPARTMENT HEAD.
I HAVE TO BE.
>> NONETHELESS.
>> MS. KNOPE.
>> YES.
>> YOU'RE HERE
BECAUSE YOU ALLEGEDLY
ACCEPTED A GIFT
OF OVER $25
AND CONTRIBUTED
TO THE DELINQUENCY OF A MINOR.
CAN YOU TELL US
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I'M GONNA TAKE A GLASS
OF WATER FIRST IF I MAY.
>> CERTAINLY.
[glass rattling]
SORRY.
>> [refreshed sigh]
"TWO DAYS AGO I ATTENDED
AN INFORMAL BOYS' CLUB MEETING
"FOR THE VERY FIRST TIME.
"AFTER ONE AND A HALF BEERS,
"AWASH IN THE GLOW
OF ACCEPTANCE
INTO THIS ELITE,
EXCLUSIVE CLUB--"
>> SORRY,
WHAT CLUB IS THIS?
>> A COUPLE CITY PLANNERS
LIKE TO DRINK BEER
IN THE COURTYARD
ON TUESDAY NIGHTS.
>> NO ONE IS SUPPOSED TO DRINK
ALCOHOL ON GOVERNMENT PROPERTY.
>> IT'S NOT MY DEPARTMENT.
GO AHEAD, LESLIE.
>> "I MADE
A VERY UNWISE DECISION,
"A DECISION THAT WILL LIVE
IN INFAMY.
"I OPENED A GIFT BASKET
OF WINE AND CHEESE.
"OUR INTERN, APRIL LUDGATE,
"DRANK SOME OF THAT WINE
WITHOUT MY KNOWLEDGE.
"THAT WAS NEVER PART
OF THE PLAN.
"SHE HAD NOT BEEN INVITED TO
THE MEETING OF THE BOYS' CLUB.
"I REPEAT,
NOT BEEN INVITED.
"THOUGH IT IS MY HOPE
THAT SOMEDAY
"SHE LIVES IN A WORLD
"WHERE THE VERY IDEA
OF BOYS' CLUBS
IS ANCIENT HISTORY."
>> BUT YOU DID
OPEN THE GIFT BASKET.
AND THE INTERN
DID DRINK THE WINE.
>> PLEASE DON'T BLAME HER
FOR MY MISTAKE.
THE BIGGEST CRIME
WE COULD COMMIT HERE
WOULD BE TO DESTROY
A TEENAGE GIRL'S PASSION
FOR LOCAL GOVERNMENT.
>> THERE'S ONLY ONE MORE THING
I NEED TO CLEAN--
ME.
UM, I CAN'T REALLY
GET INTO A SHOWER,
SO I GOT THIS IDEA
FROM MY PARENTS.
THIS IS HOW
THEY CLEAN THEIR DOG.
[humming]
[chuckles]
YOU LIKE THAT?
* WHERE'S MY BABY AT
I WROTE THAT FOR ANN.
IT'S GONNA BE PLAYING WHEN SHE
WALKS THROUGH THE DOOR TODAY.
AND CHECK THIS OUT.
WASHED MY SHORTS.
HOW DO YOU LIKE THAT?
[gate opens]
>> HEY, TURN THAT DOWN.
>> NO.
I WROTE THAT SONG.
>> I DON'T CARE.
TURN IT DOWN.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN MY YARD, LAWRENCE?
GET OUTTA HERE.
>> OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT,
I'M TAKING IT.
>> PUT DOWN MY BOOM BOX.
>> IT'S MY BOOM BOX NOW.
I ASKED YOU NICELY.
>> YOU DID NOT ASK ME NICELY.
PUT THAT DOWN!
I JUST PUT 12 NEW BATTERIES
IN THAT THING!
* I LOOK TO THE EAST
LAWRENCE, COME ON.
>> [imitating Andy] UGH, UGH.
>> GIVE IT TO ME.
GO BACK INSIDE, HANK.
>> MS. KNOPE, WHAT WAS
THE FIRST THING YOU DID
WHEN YOU ARRIVED AT WORK
THE NEXT DAY?
CAN YOU GO OVER THE TIMELINE
FOR US ONCE MORE?
>> YES, OF COURSE.
I AWOKE AT 6:21 A.M.
AFTER A FITFUL NIGHT OF SLEEP.
>> WE'VE BEEN OVER THIS.
WHAT MORE COULD YOU GUYS
POSSIBLY WANT HER TO DO?
>> WELL, WE DON'T KNOW YET.
FRANKLY, WE'VE GOT
A LOT MORE QUESTIONS.
>> [groans]
>> RON, IT'S OKAY.
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
THIS IS NOT COMMUNIST CHINA.
YOU CANNOT
MAKE HER WHIP HERSELF.
YOU CANNOT MAKE HER
WEAR A HAIR SHIRT.
>> WE WEREN'T PLANNING
ON DOING EITHER OF THOSE THINGS.
>> THIS IS AMERICA.
YOU WANNA LIVE
IN NORTH KOREA,
YOU CAN LIVE IN NORTH KOREA.
I DON'T WANT TO.
I WANT TO LIVE IN AMERICA.
LESLIE HAS NEVER BROKEN
A RULE IN HER LIFE,
TO THE POINT
THAT IT'S ANNOYING.
IF YOU WANT TO SLAP HER
ON THE WRIST, GO AHEAD.
YOU WANNA
DO ANYTHING MORE SERIOUS,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO GO THROUGH ME.
LET'S GO.
>> ARE WE DONE?
>> WE'RE DONE.
LET'S GO.
SO AFTER ALL THAT,
IT'S REALLY NOT THAT BAD.
YOU'RE GONNA GET A LETTER
IN YOUR FILE.
>> RON, I JUST WANTED
TO SAY THANK YOU--
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
NO, I DIDN'T DO IT
FOR LESLIE.
I DID IT BECAUSE
I HATE BUREAUCRACY.
MY IDEA
OF A PERFECT GOVERNMENT
IS ONE GUY WHO SITS
IN A SMALL ROOM AT A DESK,
AND THE ONLY THING
HE'S ALLOWED TO DECIDE
IS WHO TO NUKE.
THE MAN IS CHOSEN
BASED ON SOME KIND OF IQ TEST
AND MAYBE ALSO
A PHYSICAL TOURNAMENT,
LIKE A DECATHLON.
AND WOMEN ARE
BROUGHT TO HIM MAYBE
WHEN HE DESIRES THEM.
>> OH, HEY, ANN,
YOU'RE HERE.
>> YEAH, I CAME
FROM THE HOSPITAL.
HOW'D IT GO?
>> I DON'T WANNA
BE OVERDRAMATIC,
BUT TODAY FELT LIKE
100 YEARS IN HELL
AND THE ABSOLUTE WORST DAY
OF MY LIFE.
>> OH, GOD.
>> I NEVER SHOULDA OPENED
THAT STUPID BASKET.
>> YEAH, WHY DID YOU
OPEN THAT BASKET?
IT DOESN'T REALLY
SEEM LIKE YOU.
>> I THINK IT'S 'CAUSE I WANTED
TO SHATTER THE GLASS CEILING,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
AND JUST KIND OF INFILTRATE
THE BOYS' CLUB.
>> HMM.
>> I DID IT FOR A GUY.
>> OH.
>> YEAH.
MARK.
>> OH.
OH, WOW.
>> WELL, I--
WE HAD A BRIEF AFFAIR
IN FEBRUARY
OF 2004.
AND, UM, THERE'S STILL
SOMETHING VERY COMPLICATED
BETWEEN US, SO.
>> YEAH, SURE.
>> YEAH.
>> SMART WOMAN.
IFFY CHOICE IN MEN.
BUT THEN AGAIN,
I'M NOT ONE TO TALK.
[gasps]
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> ANDY, THIS IS SO SWEET.
>> NOTHING.
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
>> OH, I WAS CHASING
OUR NEIGHBOR
WHO IS A TOTAL JAG-WEED.
AND I FELL
IN SOME PRICKLY BUSHES.
DOESN'T MATTER.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THE HOUSE?
HMM?
WERE YOU TOTALLY SURPRISED?
>> YEAH.
>> DO YOU LOVE IT?
HERE, BABY, SIT DOWN.
I'M GONNA PUT SOMETHING
ON THOSE SCRATCHES.
>> SOMEBODY IS GETTING
GENTLY LAID TONIGHT.
>> ANDY, GOD.
>> YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU NEED ONE OF THESE.
>> [sighs]
>> COME ON.
YOU'RE OVER 21.
>> NOT SUPPOSED TO BE DRINKING
ON GOVERNMENT PROPERTY.
LOOSEN UP.
YOU'RE GONNA
DRIVE YOURSELF CRAZY
TRYING TO FOLLOW EVERY SINGLE
RULE IN GOVERNMENT.
>> MARK, I HAVE A LETTER
IN MY FILE.
>> I GOT SEVEN LETTERS
PRETTY MUCH EVERY GUY
IN CITY PLANNING
HAS A BUNCH OF LETTERS.
SO WELCOME TO THE TEAM.
[bottles clink]
>> LOOK OUT, BOYS.
I'M IN YOUR CLUB NOW.
I'M IN YOUR CLUB.
I'M IN YOUR--UM, CREEPY.