Well,one of The funner things
That we do that we do Here in pawnee
Is the annl Easter egg hunt.
Tom hides the eggs, And,i have to say,
He did an exceptional Job this year.
I've been searching For 25 minutes,
And i haven't found A single egg.
And i'm an adult.
O,yeah,I forgot to do that.
Maybe tom's trying To
make this year a challenge.
And if so,He's--
he's succeeding.
I don't think a single
egg Has been found yet.
Let's keep looking.
We're gonna find one.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Proudly Presents
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Sync: YTET-¿¨»Ò
Parks and Recreation
S01 E02
I'm going To see my mom.
She's a big mucky-muck In
the county school system.
She's my hero.
How do i explain her?
She's as respected As mother teresa,
She's as powerful As stalin,
And she's as beautiful
As margaret thatcher.
In or out,leslie. Doorway is creepy.
Right,sorry. Choosing in.
So,what do you want,Leslie?
Just here to
gossip,Gab,chat. Stuff we do.
But it looks Like you're super-busy.
And i am super-busy,
So i shall bid you adi.
Oh,that's weird.
I just rembered something.
I have My own subcommittee now.
Yeah. I'm sure you've
heard Something about it.
People are talking About it.
No.  Oh,well.
Anyway,we're having A town hall meeting
Tomoow at 7:00 p.m.
At the smithfield Community center.
Yeah,i'm leading it.
It's no biggy.
I mean,it is. It's a big deal,i mean...
I don't know,I mean,you know...
Wanna come?
Oh,honey,jeez,You know how busi am.
I know. I know. I know.
That's why i fake-invited you.
I'll try to be there.
Okay,so everybody's here.
Let's get started.
Sorry. Oh,i'm sorry.
Metal. Sorry.  It was relyoud.
Subcommittee members,are we
Prepared for tomorrow night?
- Tom,have you booked The hall yet?
- Yes,sir.
Ann,did you clear Your schedule?
I did. I changed my shift. Okay.
Leslie,i just have to say
I think You might be taking this
To the public A little bit too soon.
It literally doesn't matter
What you propose to the public,
They might call for a vote.
And if they vote you
down,Then you're done.
I don't care If there's gonna be a vote.
I have a secret weapon.
Canvassing.
Nothing better Than good
old-fashioned Door-to-door campaigning.
I'm not above using My expertise
To change hearts and
minds If the cause is just.
When i was in sixth grade,
I was voted best dressed By 87 votes.
And there were only
63 people In my class.
Andy fell into that pit.
I fell into that pit.
How many more pawnee citizens
Are going to have to fall
Into that pit Before we turn it to park?
Zero. Say it.
- zero.
- A hundred.
I've got some sunscreen
For your beaks.
Tom,you probably Won't need any.
Uh,and this is Our canvassing guide.
This is gonna be the script
That we use When we speak with people.
"if a person is a man,Turn to page two."
"if the person looks
Like a celebrity--
Jack nicholson-- Use
this to help your pitch.
You can't handle The pit.
That's why we need to
turn it Into a park."
O this is really thorough.
Ann and i are a team.
You guys are a team.
We have even sectors.
You guys have odd sectors.
And we're gonna win.
- Yeah.
- Win what?
Go!
Okay. Oh,someone's in there.
This is gonna be fun. Are you excited?
- Excited,yeah.
-  Are you ready?
- Yes,definitely.
- Are you pumped up?
- Yes.
- Look humble.
But confident.
Good afternoon. We are representatives
From your local government.
May we speak with you For a moment
- About the sullivan street pit?
- Sure.
Excellent. Potive response.
How would you feel If we turned that pit
Into a beautiful community park?
Oh,yeah,That would be a great idea.
Oh,good,i actually live
In the neighborhood,
So i could probably tell
you A little bit about...
Hey,tut-tut-tut.
Section three.
Okay,Um,we are having
A public forum Tomorrow night.
Lde great If you could come voice
Your strong support.
Tomorrow? I can't.
I'm busy. Sorry.
Oh,yes,we understand
That people are busy,
But we would love for you
To come to the meeting--
- Sorry.
- Good luck,though. I'm all for a park.
Would it change your
mind If we told you that--
She's gone.
Yeah,a park,huh? That sounds
Like a really good idea.
Great. Would you be willing To come
- To a town meeting And show
your support? Absolutely.
Now,is this park gonna have A playground
Or,you know,maybe a pool For the kids?
Oh,how old are your kids?
No kids.
- I'm gonna put him down As a yes.
- Don't do that.
Also is the park gonna be
At least a thousand feet From my house?
Because,yeah,I really can't move again.
April,please stand Behind me.
That's it. That's all that we got.
- No flier?
- Nope.
Okay. Thank you.
Oh,man,this is great. This is so great.
I love canvassing.
What a great way To spend my time.
All right,team haverford,
You guys are awesome,But
i think i might work better
As a solo artist,So
i'm gonna head ou Peace.
He runs weird.  He really does.
It's a good idea.
But i'm just not sure.
Okay,which part Are you not sure about?
Turning the pit Into a park.
That's kind of The whole thing.
Look,i think This is a great idea,
But i can't make Any forum.
I would have to get A babysitter.
How old are your kids?
Four and two.
- Could the four-year-old
Watch the two-year-old? - Oy.
Mickey!
What's up,buddy?
How's my number one sod man Doing?
Look,here's the one,two,three
Of the situation.
We're building A new park.
I'm on the committee.
You're putting In the sod.
And who knows,You
know,maybe down the line,
Situation will arise
Where you could hook me up.
Are you gonna coito coming
To this meeting tomorrow
Or are you gonna be a bitch?
Yes,you do owe me. Tom haverford.
Okay,keep going. Keep moving.
Nose to the grindstone.
- No means yes.
- can we stop,please?
Because it's really hot And i'm tired.
Yeah,i'm hot too.
Let's blow In each other's faces.
- Or we could drink some water.
- Yeah,let's do that.
My house is really close by.
Let's ju gtio ontake a
break For an hour or so.
Okay,okay,look,i didn't Want
it to have to come to this,
But,ann,please open the sealed
Envelope that's in your binder.
This is a little something
I learned from karl rove.
If you want to guarantee
The results of a survey,
You design the question
To give you the answer That you want.
"wouldn't you rather have A park
Than a storage facility
For nuclear waste?"
That seems iffy.
Yeah,don't worry about
it. I made it all up.
Yeah,that's--
That's what i mean.
Wouldn't you agree,
Like most decent aricans,
That it would be a good idea To turn
The abandoned lot On sullivan street
Into a beautiful community park?
Oh,actually,no.
I'm not really a fan Of parks.
Very noisy. Barbecue smell all the time.
Would you change your mind If i told you
That nine out of ten meth
users Said the same exacthing?
What?
How would you even know that?
Survey.
We surveyed crystal meth users.
We're actually having
A little town meeting tomorrow
Night if you wanted to...
Okay,look,i know It snds weird,
But i just don't like Living near parks.
So do you have a flier Or something?
I'd be happy to take it.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
You don't care About your kids
If you don't support this park.
Excuse me?
It's-- what
i mean is,
Kids love parks And you should too.
So if i don't support
Your little project,
Then i don't love my daughter?
I didn't...
What time is this thing Anyway?
Ah,it's next month. Forget it.
Oh,it's tomorrow night. I'll be there.
- Great.
- Okay,come on.
- We got one.
- Come on.
Am i talking to
The two sexit thighs In landscaping?
Yes,i am,'Cause i'm talking to marcy.
How's it going? Tom haverford.
Kevin,Your sandboxes are the best.
That's why i want you involved.
I just want the best monkey
bars I can get in my park.
I don't mind hooking you up.
Maybe down the line,There
will be a situation
Where you can hook me up.
Thank you for your time,Sir.
Well,he said Some upsetting things.
I can't believe you gave
him Your home phone number.
Well,i'm a public servant.
I need to be accessible.
What the hell is wrong With people?
I should show them Andy's medical bills.
Maybe they'd have A little sympathy.
Oh,my god. Ann,game changer.
You just busted the game Wide open.
- How?
- Andy. We need andy. He's our symbol.
We'll wheel him around the
Neighborhood to get sympathy.
He's a cute fdr.
- Yeah.
Ron,you got minute.
Uh,sure,paul. What can i do for you?
Sullivan street park project,You
fast-tracked it,right?
Yeah,absolutely.
Uh,we have A public forum tomorrow.
Okay,great. I'll be there.
Great. Okay.
"you fast-tracked that,right?"
- I'm sorry. Did you say something?
- No.
- You didn't say anything To me?
There's a new wind blowing
In government,And i don't like it.
All of a sudden,there's all
This federal money coming in,
And paul,the city manager,Is telling us
To build parks,Start
new community programs.
It's horrifying.
Do you have Like a nurse's costume?
Costume? You meanike scrubs?
- Yeah,put those on.
- Okay.
Please tell me
Please tell me why
My car is In
the front yard--
Bass,come on!
And i'm sleeping With my clothes on
I came in Through the window
Last night
- It can
bericky--  - Don't.
Why do i want to build This park so bad?
Maybe because a pit filled
With garbage isn't the best
That we can do In america.
You know,in russia,
They could pretend That pit was a park.
Bring their kids down there.
"hey,vlad,Look at these rocks.
"let's pretend They're potatoes.
"nikolai,
Do you want to swim In the dirt?"
But not here,okay?
'Cause we're a nation Of dreamers.
And it is my dream
To build a park
At i one day visit With
my white house staff
On my birthday.
And they say,"president
knope,This park is awesome.
"now we understand why you are The first
female president Of the united states."
Leslie knope.
Builder of parks.
How was canvassing?
Canvassing was okay.
But i think we're going to have To
postpone the town meeting.
Postpone?
Only for 1 to 90 days.
No,you're doing This meeting.
Yohave my full support.
I was talking To the city manager,
Exchanging ideas.
There's a mutual respect There.
And,together,we have decided
To fast-track your project.
City manager? Wow,really?
I have to cancel this meeting.
Fast-track?
Did my ne come up at all?
Oh,this meeting needs To be canceled.
No,it's happening.
Look,just-- just do
a good job Tomorrow.
Okay,we have to push This thing through.
Of course,Of course.
I'll push anything Through anything.
You know me.
Are you sweating Through your suit?
I doubt it. It's a
very breathable fabr-
Oh,yeah,i am.
- Jerry,
- what's up,man?
Hey,you're into pretzels,Right?
Bam! Hit 'em up,man.
Thanks for coming down.
I got a seat taped
off for you Over there.
****missing****
Getting your fences in there.
I drove by one of your
fences The other day.
I was like,man,That fence looks awesome.
I was like,of course,Roy's.
If you're Into chocolate muffins,
Grab as many as you want.
Some people may say that
Bringing in these contractors
This early is jumping
the gun A little bit.
Well,guess what? Here's the gun.
Here's me. Boom.
Victor miles,tom haverford. How are you?
Thank you so much For coming down.
I want to introduce you To leslie.
- Victor miles.
- Hi.
He's a gentleman i met Canvassing.
He also happens to be
The top sod guy indiana.
- That's terrific.
- Hey,les. Hey.
I really want you To nail this. Yeah?
Don from don's cement,Tom haverford.
Good to see you.
Just thinking of a
jingle For your company.
How's this? Don's cement Is
the best you can get Don's
Oh,i'm so glad You're here.
Yeah,andy came too To give support.
I have a lot Of stage experience,so...
This'll be fine,right?
It's a park,For god's sakes.
How much can they hate a park?
A lot of them seemed to
hate A park yesterday.
- April,april,i need you In the audience.
- Okay.
Wait. And if the questions
start Tting negative,
I'm gonna call on you,
And i need you to sell the cra Park anou
- Can you do that?
- Why?
Please,april,This is serious.
- Can you do that?
- Probably.
Good girl,good girl.
Good probably. Good girl.
Okay,here we go. Line up,everybody.
My mom's here.
Oh,no,i can't do that.
That's illegal.
Thank you so much For
coming out tonight.
This is our first ti
About the proposal To turn lot 48
On sullivan street In a community park.
Yeah!
This is gonna be A train wreck.
I want my daughter To be successful.
Which is why i always tell her,
"there's nothing wrong With
being a wife and mother."
Now,there are many
people That i spoke to
Who are passionately
in support Of this idea.
None of them were able
To make it tonight,
Unfortunately.
But they totally exist.
I did not make them up.
Oh,i see a question. Okay.
No,no.
No. No questions right now.
- My name is kate speevack...
- I remember you.
And i live In the neighborhood.
And i am 100% Against this park.
I cannot believe the
department Is moving forward
With a project without a single
Environmental impact study.
And if you guys agree With me,
Let's ke a stand.
Okay.
Um,we are a little ahead Of schedule
Because we're holding This
town hall meeting so soon.
Which i was warned about
By mark brendanawicz,
Our city planner
Assigned to this project.
Uh,so what would he say?
Here we are.
Leslie,should i give them
Some background info On the site?
Absolutely,okay.
Mark brendanawicz knows The
answer to every question.
He's amazing,And congratulations
for hearing Him speak.
Hi,there. Leslie might have
Oversold me a little bit.
Certainly did not. He's the man.
He's capable of anything. Okay.
Lot 48 is,uh,It's a rectangular lot.
It's got excellent drainage,
And it's on the corner
Of sullivan and collins.
Any questions?
I have more of a
comment Than a question.
- Go for it.
- It's for the guy in the cast.
Here we go. Lawrence.
Yes,yes,yes.
That is andy dwyer.
He is a local resident,and
He tragicay ll in the pit.
Uh,yeah,i don't care About any of that.
He's the guy that plays
music All night in his garage.
It's driving me nuts.
Lawrence lives With his grandma.
Which is pretty awesome.
He takes care ofer,i guess.
But whatever. He's a douche bag.
It's loud. It's abusive.
And it's waking up My birds.
You have birds now?
Yeah,i have birds.
I have nice,pretty,Expensive birds.
And you play that
music,And it wakes them up.
Look,i don't work For
the government,okay.
Uh,i do py rock & roll.
Guilty as charged.
I'm in a band.
It's called just the tip.
And,actually,If anyone here
plays bass,We need a bassist.
Yes,okay,let's take A
five-minute break,shall we?
Uh,it is not going well At all.
It's going very poorly.
Okay,like you're crashing And burning.
Democracy's happening.
People are talking.
I mean,at least They
aren't apathetic,right?
You're right about that.
They're deeply negative.
You need to put a happy face On this,
Give me A few positive talking points.
And whatever you do,Avd a vote.
I'm oddly attracted To kate speevack.
Before we continue,I'd
love to just give you
A little history of wnee.
The city of pawnee Was
incorporated in 1817
When a young man by the name
Of reverend luther howell
Came from terre haute On an ox.
He planted his flag In
the ground and was met
Soon aft by an angry
tribe Of wamapoke indians,
Who,when seeing the
whiteness Of his skin,
Twisted him to death.
Flash forward to 1969.
Man walks on the moon.
Pawnee is lousy With hippies...
My god,she's filibustering
Her own meeting.
Mod squad--
Filibuster. Boom.
They can't touch you
If you talk forever.
I can't speak of the future.
But i will.
The future of pawnee will
Involve us flying around
In space taxis Where we will communicate
On watches and blink Our
feelings to each other
Rather than use words.
And now i'd like to take
A magical journey
Through a little something
I like to call The phantom tollbooth
By norton juster.
Excuse me,can't you read
That children's book On your own time?
I have the floor.
"there once was a boy Named milo
"who didn't know what
to do With himself.
Not just
sometimes,But always"--
Okay,all right,You know
what, This is a public forum,
Which means that we all get
To tell you what we think.
Well,you did already talk,Ma'am.
And i would love To
listen to someone else,
Someone i don't know.
Uh,that girl over there
With the long brown
hair And the yellow top.
Could you tell us how
you feel About this park?
- Go ahead.
- Hi.
Uh,i'm a youth In the community,
And i think a new park Is a great ia.
And i fully support it,
As would the rest of the
youth In the community.
Hey,i recognize her.
That kid came to my door Yesterday.
Oh,my god,okay,they have
Planted people in this audience.
Unbelievable.
U know what,we all agree
That this park is a baidea.
We should just take a vote.
- Right?
- Okay,we will take a vote Before we do that,
I want everyone up,Lined
up behind that microphone.
I want to hear from
all of you,One-by-one.
That was brutal.
A couple weeks ago,I was yelling
At leslie At a public forum.
God,i hope i wasn't As
obnoxious as those people.
I wasn't,right?
At 5:00 in the
morning,Every morning--
Beep,beep,beep-- I
don't want to hear that.
Now,how long Is this project gonna take?
That's what i wanna know.
That's what's important to me.
Because i need my sleep.
Thank you,ma'am. Thank you,ma'am.
That concludes our meeting.
What abouthvote?
We're out of time. It's 9:00.
But we will have many
Public forums in the future,
And we hope To see you all there.
Thank you so much For coming.
It was tough.
But,you know,that's
pawnee. That's democracy.
There are a lot of people
here That want this park.
You just gotta get past
The negative people.
But guess what?
My subcommittee held its First
town hall meeting tonight.
God,i loved it.
I loved every minute of it.
Hey,park lady.
- Yeah?
- You suck.
Hear that?
He called me park lady.
You know,normally,
I don't agree with
leslie About anything,
****missing****