When I started goop in 2008,
I was like, "My calling is something else
besides, you know,
making out with Matt Damon
on screen or whatever."
[laughs]
And now, it's this modern lifestyle brand.
To me, it's all laddering up to one thing,
which is optimization of self.
Like, we're here one time, one life.
Like, how can we really, like,
milk the shit out of this?
[laughing]
You have a hundred needles
in your face, Elise.
- Just another day at the office.
- [laughing]
The opportunity that we have
with the goop lab,
is that, as a company, we can go out
in different groups
and go on a much deeper dive
into some of these topics
- that our readers are curious about.
- [laughing]
This is gonna be my first experience
- with mushrooms.
- [woman] Oh!
- [exhales]
- [woman] You have to let go of your ego.
[Gwyneth Paltrow]
So what happens in a workshop?
- Everyone gets off.
- [woman moaning]
What the fuck are you doing to people?
[man vocalizing]
We get to explore, like, "Is this real?
Do we feel better?"
And grapple with some topics that are hard
and embarrassing or shameful.
- Isn't that beautiful? Relax.
- [exhales]
That was, like, next level shit.
So, are you guys ready to go out
in the field
- and make a ruckus?
- [Elise Loehnen] Yeah.
- You can handle it, right?
- [laughing]
[theme music playing]
[Betty Dodson] Hand over hand.
You want to focus on your breathing.
You want to focus
on the sensation in your vulva,
and you want to focus
on your body's movement.
[Carlin Ross]
Orgasms don't drop down from heaven.
[Gwyneth] For men,
it does drop out of the sky,
and for women, it's a different,
much different experience.
[Elise] I would imagine
a vast majority of women
have experienced shame
around their own pleasure.
I was feeling weird
even letting the person,
like my partner, touch me during sex.
[Elise] It's really about the connection
you have with yourself.
I have never done the whole mirror,
what's happening down there.
You've never seen yourself?
- No.
- [Betty] Come over here.
[laughing]
- [Carlin] We teach women how to orgasm.
- Wow.
- So, could you flip over my hand?
- [woman] Yeah.
[Carlin] Say what you need.
That's very, very hard for women.
[Betty] We have to have self
to be able to take control.
So, have a healthy sexual relationship
with yourself,
so that you're coming
to your sexual partner
as an active participant
in your sexual experience.
- To say what they want.
- We used to say...
that a woman had to learn how
to "run the fuck."
- Wow.
- [laughs]
[Betty] And if you can't say it,
you're in trouble.
"Run the fuck."
[laughing]
- [Betty] Are you blushing?
- Yes.
[laughing]
[Gwyneth] Okay.
- Are you ready to talk about vaginas?
- I'll run.
- It's our favorite subject.
- Who?
- Vaginas!
- [laughing]
The vagina's the birth canal only.
You want to talk about the vulva,
which is the clitoris and the inner lips
and all that good shit around it.
[laughing]
- The vagina is only the birth canal?
- [Betty] Birth canal.
Oh. See, I'm getting an anatomy lesson
that I didn't...
I thought the vagina was the whole...
No, no, no.
[Carlin] That's why Betty's focus
has always been on vulva.
That's everything
that makes you feel good,
so that's her pet peeve
with vulva versus vagina. [laughs]
How long have you been doing this work?
Forever.
I mean, I'm already 90.
So, what happens in a workshop?
- Everyone gets off.
- [laughing]
[Carlin] We answer the door naked,
'cause I want them
to know I'm being vulnerable
'cause I'm asking you to be vulnerable.
And then we get naked
and we sit in a circle.
Sign me up. [laughing]
Sign me out.
Like, naked in a room
with a bunch of women?
I don't know if I have the guts.
There's no judgment.
It's acceptance of our bodies.
And what you'll see is
when you look around the room...
everyone's beautiful.
Yeah.
Shame, I think pervades
so much of our sexuality.
I can't think of anything
more demanding you to be shame-free
than sitting naked in a room
with other women.
[laughing]
All of that goes away immediately.
- [Gwyneth] Right.
- It really does.
I have days when I go,
"Ugh. The skin doesn't fit.
It's all blotchy.
I got all these bruises."
I could carry on and on and on.
I can walk. I can talk. I can see.
I still can have orgasms,
so why would I want to complain
about a wrinkle or whatever?
I kind of want to do this.
- I dare you to do it.
- [laughing]
I might do it. I might show up.
[Carlin] That would be great.
Put a group together here
and I'll come back and lead one.
- Uh-oh. It's an HR crisis.
- Should we do it?
[laughing]
So, how important do you think it is
for women clothed, unclothed
to be having these conversations?
I think it's everything.
I mean, sisterhood, I can't imagine...
Not being able to talk.
Not being able to be with a group of women
a couple of times of the year,
just to recharge and just to connect.
I mean, there's something
so powerful about it.
- And healing at the same time.
- Yeah.
A group of goop staffers
did a different workshop,
fully clothed, where they explored
being in their bodies,
learning how to ask
for what they want and need.
[Betty] Oh, amazing.
[Megan]
I wanted to take part in this workshop
because I'm married, and it's wonderful,
but I think intimacy is hard,
even when you love someone
and you're really close.
Sex education for me
was me learning from encyclopedias
and learning through rumors.
Even when I started
to come into my own as a woman,
I still didn't have any education
about pleasure.
We have a long way to go,
and I think starting to talk about this
is the right way to do it.
Welcome, everybody.
I'm super excited that you're here today
and that you're gonna prioritize
your pleasure and your sensuality
and your connection with yourself.
Let's share what our biggest challenge is
in the realm of sexuality,
body, self, sex shame...
I would like to feel more sensual
just in general
and have it not be contingent
on compliments
and other people and the perception
of what sexy and sensual is.
Similar to Megan, I would really like
to feel sensual at work
or when I'm cooking
or when I'm being creative.
Some days I feel like a blob.
I feel like, you know, this, that.
And for me,
it's very much associated with my body.
[Isabella] Okay, so there's
some body shame.
Exactly, like, if I ran that morning...
or I didn't, or you know,
something like that
or my clothes aren't fitting
like I want it to.
[Isabella] Do you feel like
you have to earn
- having a positive body image?
- Exactly.
- Okay.
- I think 100% for me.
We feel ashamed to, like,
talk about women having sexual needs
and wants and things like that,
and you don't talk about it
with your friends.
No one talks about it in school,
about pleasure just in general.
So, you don't learn about it,
and you grow up thinking
it's something that you keep in,
and you keep it to yourself.
In the long run, you don't end up
sharing that with your partner,
who you want to experience that with.
So then it just gets locked in,
closed up...
[laughs] Hi, ladies. I'm Lexi.
When I first heard that goop
was doing this episode
about female pleasure,
I was like, "I have to participate in it,"
because I have personally struggled
with sexual wellness.
I grew up in Shanghai,
where sex wasn't talked about,
and I have never really talked
to my parents
about sex or my sexuality,
being a gay woman,
so I didn't really know what sex was.
goop is such a safe environment
for me to explore my sexual wellness,
and goop has been very supportive
of this topic as well.
In my past relationships with other women,
I was the one who was
mostly giving in the sexual relationship.
I was feeling weird
even letting my partner touch me
during sex,
or even... I was like,
"I want to turn the light off."
I don't want the light on.
I just feel a little bit of disconnect
with my body,
and I feel like I think I want
to be able to receive.
[Isabella] You have all earned the right
to feel good in your body
and to feel sensual.
There is absolutely nothing
that you need to do to earn that.
You can work out 'cause you feel strong.
[Heaven] Yeah.
[Isabella] That needs to be very separate
from the way you see yourself.
So many of us women are caught
in this paradigm
that we have to look a certain way
and, you know,
we're so critical of ourselves.
It's funny 'cause I'm not critical
of another woman's body,
but I'm so critical of my own body.
[Carlin] That's true for, like,
every woman.
For hundreds of years,
men have been painting, sculpting
and photographing women,
and the second
you put a camera in her hand,
it becomes vain,
because people are uncomfortable
when you say, "I feel beautiful."
So, let's get into our sensual vibes
and then we're gonna take
our portraits together.
- Yeah.
- Awesome!
Are you ready?
- Yeah. I think so.
- [Isabella] Okay.
So, this is a time for you
to just express yourself however you want.
Sensual self-portraits
are a visual representation
of your sexual relationship with yourself.
It's important to be in charge
of how you feel as a sensual creature.
Three, two, one, beautiful.
[Lexi] I've been through some body issues,
and I have struggled
to put myself out there
and share my own body.
[Isabella] Oh, my God, you look so strong!
You look like you're fierce,
like you're about to start running.
[Lexi] I just want to be me.
I just wanna be happy
and do what I want to do.
[Isabella] Love it.
Which is your favorite one, do you think?
- I like all of 'em.
- Yay! I love it.
[Lexi] This is, like,
the most authentic self.
I enjoy working out. I love boxing...
Yeah, it makes me feel more confident,
sexier, more sensual,
like I'm taking care of myself,
like, having fun too at the same time.
[Isabella] It's beautiful.
[gull squawking]
I wonder how much disassociation
you guys see
of women from their bodies.
Oh, complete... Yes.
[Betty] And in the female genitals.
You hear the same stories,
and it's always like,
you know, "I'm dirty down there."
There is always this genital shame
that happens when...
Wow. Why? Where do we get that?
[Betty] The culture.
Think of all the nicknames,
"pussy, snatch."
- [Carlin] It's not very positive.
- Right.
[Carlin] Even just the language by itself.
[Gwyneth] My boy turned 13 yesterday.
You know, when I think about the access
he has to pornography,
like the way that women are portrayed
in pornography.
Yeah, the women lie there,
and they have a certain look,
and their genitals are surgically altered.
Really?
[Carlin] Most women
have dangling inner lips
- and what they do is they cut the labia.
- Oh, my God.
- [Carlin] And they bleach everything pink.
- I've never heard this before.
So, everyone looks like a baby doll.
They look like a teen girl.
[Gwyneth] Like a Barbie.
That's why women come in and they're like,
"There's something wrong.
I have dark inner lips,"
or "they're not symmetrical."
I had the good fortune
to have a very curious, intelligent lover,
and he wanted to look at me, and I went,
"Oh, no, I'd rather you wouldn't."
He said, "Why not?"
And I said, "I'm deformed."
I was a grown woman
thinking I was sexually deformed
that my vulva had these long inner lips.
I didn't think it was normal.
And he said,
"Honey, you're perfectly normal."
And he went and got these books
that he used to masturbate to.
And he pointed.
He said, "There's one like you,
and another...
Oh, and there's another one."
So, it was such a revelation to me.
And so, from that day on,
my sex life improved.
I didn't feel the shame,
and shame is a killer of pleasure.
So, that's when I started
doing the workshops.
And I realized women
didn't know their own body.
We don't have many examples
of what a real vagina... vulva.
Excuse me, pardon me. Vulva, vulva, vulva.
- [Betty] Very good.
- [Gwyneth] Thank you.
- What it looks like.
- No.
The theory of the workshop,
it's to get women, first vulnerable...
- [Betty] Yes.
- Comfortable in their body,
- comfortable with their vulva.
- Mm-hmm.
It's gonna be hard to try that word on
- and use it.
- I know. Vulva.
Vulva, vulva.
[Carlin] So I think the most important
ritual on day one
is genital show and tell.
And I think if you say,
"Okay, I'm gonna sit next to Betty Dodson,
and I'm gonna look at my vulva,
and everyone else is gonna look,
and you think, "Oh, my God."
- [laughs] What could be scarier than that?
- Right.
[laughing]
[Betty] So now we're sitting
with our genitals exposed.
No more hiding,
no more shame, no more guilt.
This is our power spot.
Come on, this is the next generation
comes from us.
Thinking about the people
who are watching the show wondering,
"Are they gonna show the vulva?"
Like, is this gonna happen?
- [laughing]
- And you think about the discomfort
that's going to start swelling
in people's bodies
at just the mere...
- I think even that...
- The thought of it.
It's just terrifying to people.
And then to get through that.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
So, now we're gonna look at it
under the light.
Get a good shot. Oh, perfect.
Isn't that beautiful?
It is.
What we're talking about
is this deep resistance we have to
- our own genitalia, culturally speaking.
- [Elise] Yeah.
It is really time for that to change.
You've looked before.
I have.
- You have to be able to see it.
- Right.
That's the whole point.
Why can't we see it?
- We see penises all the time.
- [Gwyneth] Right.
- We sure do.
- Yeah, seriously.
[laughing]
See the shape and see the form.
Wonderful.
[Carlin] So, I do groom a little.
What's so interesting here
is that you've got this pattern.
It's like an arrow, like...
[exclaims, laughs]
This is my clitoral hood...
and my clitoris isn't super big.
- [Betty] It's the glans.
- There's the glans right there.
- Oh.
- Mmm.
That's where it's all taking place, kid.
But you'd have to show more than one,
because if you only showed one,
that would become the one.
We'd all imitate it.
Shana, start filming more vulvas.
- [Elise] Yeah.
- [Shana] On it!
[laughing]
[Betty] So you need to show a variety.
[Carlin] Yeah, to see that image...
In that moment,
you know you're not alone.
There's nothing wrong with you.
How healing is that?
'Cause you can go,
"Oh, that looks like mine."
- [Elise] Yeah.
- We always think there's something wrong.
- [Elise] Hmm.
- So they get to find out that,
indeed, their vulva's perfect,
and they're all different.
- But it's one thing just to look.
- [Gwyneth] Right.
But it's also about being knowledgeable
about your body.
And then beyond that,
with the connection to pleasure,
is the workshop teaching women
how to have an orgasm
because they don't...
[Carlin] Yeah,
how to stimulate themselves.
We always say with the workshops,
"You're together, but alone."
So you're supported,
you're in a safe environment,
and this is really about
making it fun and playful.
You know, too often when we're having
any kind of sex experience,
- it's always so serious for women.
- [Gwyneth] Mm-hmm.
You're always worried about
so many things.
Right.
[Elise] Men have been fed this lie
that women should just be able
to get there or that it should be easier,
that it doesn't require work.
That can be shocking for a lot of women,
that orgasm is work.
We hear that a lot.
- "I should just orgasm, it's natural."
- Yeah.
And I think women have probably fed that
by performing potentially in a fake way.
[Gwyneth] Right.
Do you guys know what
performative receiving is?
No.
[Isabella]
Something that usually only women do.
It is a way that you either accentuate
or completely fake your pleasure,
and I'm not talking about
faking your orgasms,
and if anyone does that,
please this is the last day
that you've ever done that
in your entire life.
It is like leaving a breadcrumb trail
to your partner
of what doesn't turn you on.
And it's okay to not have
an orgasm every time.
Instead, we can have
a really lovely conversation.
"Yes, this part felt really good.
I would love to experience you
doing more of that.
This other part, mmm, maybe not so much."
Which is why we're gonna do
our next exercise, which is massage.
You can choose hand or feet.
You're gonna communicate what you like
and you're gonna negotiate consent.
It smells so good.
I like when you pull down on my fingers
and open my joints.
I think it feels really good on my joints.
- I'm gonna do one by one.
- Yeah, like that.
[Isabella] And in a sexual context,
you could say something
along the lines of,
"That last move you were doing,
or that last technique
was feeling really good.
Could we go back to that?"
Would you like a hand massage?
Yeah, let's do hands.
I'm very ticklish.
I might need a little bit more oil.
[Isabella] That's beautiful.
Good communication.
We can't receive pleasure
that we don't ask for.
Does it feel as good on the top like this
as on the sides?
- I like the top. Yeah.
- Like this one, okay.
Just being in sex
and thinking to yourself,
"Oh, I wish my partner was doing X, Y, Z,"
is not gonna make your partner do X, Y, Z.
They can't read your mind.
It is so vitally important
that you communicate your needs.
We can do this in such a loving way.
You guys are modeling it so beautifully.
The massage exercise was...
was pretty awesome
because it doesn't seem so crazy
or important,
but you realize that
to get the result you want,
you actually have to say something.
There's no magic person in the world
who knows what you want
and who can read your mind.
So it's just, it's good food for thought.
- [laughing] Thanks, Lexi.
- Namaste.
- Namaste. My hands feel so much better.
- [laughs] Namaste.
Besides not knowing our bodies,
which I am absolutely guilty of,
I have never really done the whole mirror,
what's happening down there.
You've never seen yourself?
No.
- [Betty] Come over here.
- [laughing]
I'm wearing a skirt.
But I think that I also have done work
to understand that I deserve pleasure,
and that pleasure is not shameful.
Do you feel like you deserve pleasure?
The idea that women
inherently deserve pleasure,
I feel like I'm just, at 46 years old,
- starting to knit that together.
- [Carlin] Mm-hmm.
But I think I was very much raised
in an era
where it was very much about the guy
and trying to look good for the guy
and do what the guy wanted,
like be the cool girl, you know, that...
Well, and now you're... you've always...
since you were 18,
been a universal sex symbol.
- Well.
- [laughing]
But you have to live up to that
in the bedroom, I'm sure, yeah.
Which is so...
it must be the weirdest experience.
[stammering] I think that I shut that out.
'Cause it's a fiction, right?
It's all a projection.
It's really nothing to do with me
or the quality of who I am
or the good things about me
or the bad things about me
or my own sexuality.
It's like, it's all a projection.
So, I feel very almost divorced
- from having that kind of pressure.
- Mm-hmm.
But maybe when I was younger,
I probably did.
[Elise] Yeah.
[Isabella] We've been talking a lot
about vulnerability, intimacy.
It's so much more comfortable
for people to disconnect
than it is to connect.
So, we're gonna do some eye gazing.
This is a no talking exercise.
It's really important that you don't talk.
We're gonna be looking
into each other's left eye.
Your left side is your feminine.
It's your receiving.
If you need to laugh, if you need to cry,
you can let it out
as long as it's not talking.
Let's get started.
- How did that feel for everybody?
- [sighing]
- Um...
- It was weird.
- I don't know why I cried.
- [Isabella] It was weird?
[Megan] It was hard.
It's hard to look at someone in the eye.
- You feel exposed, and you want to laugh.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
- And you just... It's uncomfortable.
[Isabella] Just that really being seen
that deeply.
Yeah.
- [Lexi] I don't know why I feel emotional.
- [Megan] You weren't sad.
- You were just emotional.
- I wasn't sad. No, it wasn't a sad moment,
and I didn't want you to freak out
or anything as I was looking.
- I was like, "What is she feeling?"
- [laughs]
But that made me
feel more connected to you,
'cause, like, I had empathy for you.
In my mind, I was telling you
it's okay to, like, let it out
and, like, just...
Yeah, it was... it was great.
Some of the activities at Belle's workshop
were very uncomfortable to me,
but it did make me realize
how important it is to be vulnerable,
be out of my comfort zone,
to communicate and practice
with my partner in different ways
to enhance our intimacy,
even if I feel awkward sometimes.
I love how you said the sort of discomfort
of not knowing how she was feeling.
It's really nice to be comfortable
in the discomfort of not knowing
how our partners
or our friends or our parents feel.
And reassuring yourself
that you're rock solid
in who you are and how you feel.
[Lexi]
I think I got some really great takeaways
on how to communicate with my partner
from the workshop,
and now I think I need
to figure out my own body
and what makes me feel good.
So, I asked goop if I could go visit
Betty Dodson in New York City.
So I heard that Lexi,
one of our star employees, came to you.
What was her experience?
When she came in,
she was definitely shaking like a leaf.
Yeah.
Hello.
[Carlin] Lexi.
- Hi, Carlin.
- You made it.
- Hi. Nice to meet you.
- It's a pleasure.
Thank you for coming.
Yeah, thanks for having me.
- Betty.
- Hello.
Legendary Betty Dodson.
- You're a tall girl.
- Hi. It's so nice to meet you.
Now I've been seeing you guys on YouTube,
- so I'm like very... yeah, it's an honor.
- [Dodson chatters]
It's an honor to meet you guys in person.
When I first heard goop
was going to do the docu-series
on this topic,
sexuality and female pleasure,
that's a topic I was more interested in.
I grew up in Shanghai.
When I grew up, it's not even okay
to like openly talk about sex,
for girls especially,
and it's not okay to be, like, sexual.
I don't think I explore my body that much.
I feel like it was shameful
to talk about, even.
- Now I'm on camera talking about it
- [laughing]
in front of millions of people,
which is great.
- [Carlin] Liberated.
- [laughs] Exactly. That's my journey.
I want everybody who are like me
or who grew up
in a more conservative culture
or even grew up here...
You know what, that's everyone,
right, Betty?
When we have women in the workshops,
there's no country in the world
that encourages girls
to explore themselves and their sexuality.
Doesn't exist.
We shut them down with the beauty myth
and the slut stigma
- and the virginity myth.
- Right.
Like, it doesn't exist.
Yeah, that's why I'm here.
- And learn how to masturbate.
- [Betty] Yay!
[Gwyneth] How many different kinds
of orgasm are there?
Is it true that there are different kinds?
Yes. The tension orgasm. [gasps]
[Carlin] That's what most people do.
I tense up, and I hold my breath,
- and then I cum.
- Right.
Or we call it the "Rock 'n Roll,"
where you...[panting]
That's Betty's technique.
You're breathing and moving,
and you're using your body naturally.
So how does that work?
You lie on your back...
And you rock?
- [laughing]
- Side to side?
- Rock.
- You rock your pelvis.
- So basically, your legs, it's like...
- [Betty] Pelvis forward.
- [laughing]
- ...your feet are on the floor
- and your legs are opened.
- [Gwyneth] Okay.
And you're rocking your pelvis forward
and when you come up,
you squeeze your PC... [inhales]
take a breath and then [exhales]
...that's it.
While you're having sex
or with a vibrator?
With a vibrator, but that will also
translate into partner sex.
If you're working that PC,
you're gonna get more blood
into your sex organ.
What is "working a PC" mean?
The pelvic floor muscle.
- You're sitting on it.
- [Gwyneth] Right.
All right, now lift up...
release.
- That is the pelvic floor muscle.
- [Gwyneth] Lift up.
Lift up, squeeze it, then let it go.
- Squeeze and release.
- Okay.
- I'm doing it. Get with the program.
- [laughing]
Elise has a full Kegel workout
in her routine.
I'm working it right now.
And remember, it's supposed to be fun
- [Gwyneth] Yes.
- and playful and feel good.
During erotic recess,
we start off with me and Betty,
and we demonstrate your
Rock 'n Roll orgasm technique,
and that's where we show you how
to combine clitoral stimulation
- with vaginal penetration.
- And the rocking.
[Carlin] So this is your
internal clitoris.
- A beautiful sex organ.
- [Lexi] Oh, my God.
[Carlin] This would be
your clitoral glans.
[Lexi] Mm-hmm.
And that's the little clit that you see
on the outside.
[Carlin] That's what most people
are touching that they say is sensitive,
but you have an internal clitoral system.
It's very complex.
These are the legs of the clitoris,
the bulbs of the clitoris.
We have as much erectile tissue as men.
We just have internal erections.
Your clitoral glans
has 8,000 nerve endings.
- [sing-songy] More than a penis.
- [laughs]
You're gonna be working your PC,
getting blood in there,
then you'll have your vibrator
on your clit.
[inhales] You're breathing,
you're rocking your pelvis.
It's a workout, but once you get going,
it's gonna take what,
20 to 40 minutes for most women?
Well, you can pop right off immediately.
So you learn to stretch it out
- 'cause the longer you have a build up,
- [Lexi] Mm-hmm.
- the bigger the orgasm.
- [Carlin] Yeah.
Do you think orgasm is important,
or do you think it's that sort of...
Abso-fucking-lutely!
[laughing]
Do you wanna go... [pants]
in front of a sneeze and then not sneeze?
Mnh-mnh.
It's a natural function of the body.
Do you think that orgasm plays a role
in women's health?
Absolutely.
[softly buzzing]
[Carlin] This is the Magic Wand.
This does not replace your partner,
- male or female, it does not.
- No.
It's an enhancement.
In the beginning, the guy's all... [gasps]
- [Lexi] Right. They're like, "Oh."
- They think this was for penetration.
Or even women, there are lesbian purists
that don't like vibrators.
This is used on the outside
for clitoral stimulation.
- What we...
- Get the barbell.
...use for penetration, this is...
Betty designed this.
It's a pound
of medical-grade stainless steel.
It's the vaginal barbell.
So what's nice about it
is when you insert it,
when you squeeze
your pelvic floor muscle,
it doesn't shoot out. It stays.
And what you'll notice and you'll see
- is when you flex your muscle...
- The weight.
The weight holds it in.
It moves.
So, it gives the women a visual
that your vagina
and your pelvic floor muscle
- is a very complicated sex organ.
- Mm-hmm.
[Carlin] It's not just a hole.
So, you always say
it's clitoral stimulation with vaginal...
- [Lexi] Both at the same time.
- Penetration.
- Yes.
- I never wanna stop doing the workshops.
- And here I am this naked, little old lady
- And you look 60.
- with her vibrator. [imitates vibrating]
- [laughing]
Maybe that's how it keeps you young.
That's how, yeah, that's how it works.
- Pleasure can't be bad.
- [Lexi] Yeah.
Yeah, it can't be bad for you.
[Gwyneth] Do you think that there's
almost a responsibility
- to show, like, what actually happens
- [Carlin] Oh, yeah.
and the beauty of a female orgasm?
[Carlin]
Yes. And to see how other women orgasm.
Not the stuff you hear on pornography,
not the stuff you see
on the Hollywood movies,
which is fake and not real.
In porn, men are, like, doing it
and women are just cumming, right?
- [Carlin] Yes.
- That's the mythology of porn?
There's no, like, reference of what
a real orgasm looks like out there.
Do you think by being
sort of explicit about it,
we can help women reframe
what that experience is?
Yes. If you could show a real live orgasm,
it would be groundbreaking.
You had kind of a one-on-one workshop?
Yes, we did a one-on-one with me,
and I could see Lexi watching everything
in the viewfinder.
And we went through the Rock 'n Roll
masturbation technique,
and I knew if we were gonna do it,
you have to go all the way, right?
And you have to have an orgasm,
so it's intimidating when you have a crew.
Oh, my God. I can't believe you did it.
- That's amazing. It's so brave.
- [Carlin] I know!
- Somebody had to.
- Right.
[Betty]
Okay, we're gonna do the Rock 'n Roll.
Thank you.
[Betty] Hand over hand.
- [Carlin] You think of, like, feminism.
- [Elise] Yeah.
Any time we took a step forward
towards equality,
it meant someone had to put it
on the line.
[Betty] Always.
Oh, I want you to take hold of it.
Yeah, just put it at the mouth
of the vagina,
just hold it there.
- Take a nice deep breath...
- [inhales]
- [exhales]
- and then relax.
[Gwyneth]
What is the inherent danger in a woman
being integrated with her sexuality?
When you're in touch with your body
and you love your body
and you can give yourself an orgasm,
you're independent.
You know who you are.
You know what you want.
We're very dangerous
when we're knowledgeable.
Tell me about it.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
- Grip the muscles, feel the weight.
- [exhaling]
You got a good strong PC muscle, kid.
Thank you.
Okay, it's all the way in.
- All the way in. Oh, good.
- Mm-hmm.
- You're working the pelvic floor muscle,
- [inhaling, exhaling]
breathing, rocking, squeezing.
That's it.
I watched the one-on-one
body sex coaching session
with Betty and Carlin.
[Betty] That's it. Let it all go.
Deep breath. Squeeze. Release.
[Lexi] I didn't know what to expect,
but when I was actually seeing it,
it was such a beautiful moment
when Betty was coaching Carlin
how to do the body movement,
those breathing techniques...
- [inhaling, exhaling]
- [vibrator buzzing]
[Betty] Beautiful.
The biggest thing that I've learned today
is that no matter who you are,
what culture you grew up in,
what country you're from,
who you identify yourself as,
it's not about you
with anyone else around you.
It's about you owning your own body.
You having a healthy,
positive relationship with your body.
Owning your own pleasure.
[Carlin moaning]
[moaning continuing]
[sighs]
[exhales]
Okay, that was fun. [laughs]
[Betty] Beautiful.
- Cut.
- [laughing, applauding]
[Carlin] All right, all right. You got it?
[woman] Oh, my God.
Well done. That was incredible.
[theme music playing]