When I started goop in 2008,
I was like, "My calling is something else
besides, you know,
making out with Matt Damon
on screen or whatever."
[laughs]
And now it's this modern lifestyle brand.
To me, it's all laddering up to one thing,
which is optimization of self.
Like, we're here one time, one life...
like, how can we really, like,
milk the shit out of this?
[laughing]
You have a hundred needles
in your face, Elise.
- Just another day at the office.
- [laughing]
The opportunity that we have
with the goop lab
is that, as a company,
we can go out in different groups
and go on a much deeper dive
into some of these topics
that our readers are curious about.
- [laughing]
- This is gonna be my first experience
- with mushrooms.
- [Gillian] Oh!
- [exhales]
- [woman] You have to let go of your ego.
[Gwyneth] So what happens in a workshop?
- Everyone gets off.
- [woman moaning]
What the fuck are you doing to people?
[man vocalizing]
We get to explore, like, is this real?
Do we feel better?
And grapple with some topics
that are hard
and embarrassing or shameful.
Isn't that beautiful?
- [exhales]
- [woman 2] Relax.
That was, like, next level shit.
So, are you guys ready
to go out in the field
- and make a ruckus?
- [Elise] Yeah.
- You can handle it, right?
- [laughing]
[Laura Lynne Jackson]
Once you become aware of your own energy
and that everything around us is energy,
you can start to do exercises and activity
that help open you up energetically.
When you open to all these abilities,
mediumship happens.
Was there just something
with your car, getting a new car?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
That's... [scoffs]
You're psychic, you're an intuitive,
you're a medium. We all are.
I could feel a vibration almost in my jaw.
I kept hearing, like, "M" popping up.
Oh, my God.
This freaks me out.
[laughs] I know you're laughing already.
To me this whole...
this whole medium, psychic world
is very much like Santa Claus.
This whole group of people
are being categorized
as unethical and fraudulent.
Ideas are laughed at
before they're accepted, right?
The world's flat, not round.
So, there's always this moment
of society being resistant
to understanding it.
If we take a piece of paper,
we're on this side, they're right here.
They're right here with us all the time.
[sighs]
It's so nice that you guys are here.
Thanks so much for having us.
- This is gonna be a good one.
- Mm-hmm.
Feel free to let us know any messages
from our deceased
- as we sit here.
- [laughing]
[Elise] So, Laura, we know you well.
You've probed both of our worlds
on the other side.
- Yes, yes.
- [Gwyneth] What is the difference
between mediums and psychics?
Being a psychic means that I read energy
and being a medium means that I can
connect with the consciousness
of people who have
left their physical bodies
and crossed to the other side.
I had had one experience
with a medium before,
and just... it hadn't resonated,
and I think I'm skeptical.
I'm like, "This is Google-able,
this is Google-able." You know?
Right, you're famous,
which is complicating.
Right, so it really complicates,
'cause you can find out
pretty much anything about me.
But when I sat down with Laura,
she was saying things
that are not Google-able.
And she knew something
that my husband didn't even know.
And then I really thought,
"Wow, this is real."
Oh, yes.
And, Julie, your research is fascinating.
Thank you.
[Elise] Why is it so important?
What happens when we die is
that affects every single person.
Yeah.
And there's a lot of anecdotal evidence
that mediumship readings help with grief.
That's certainly been my case.
So there's tens, if not hundreds,
if not thousands,
if not millions of people in the US,
at least,
who have these experiences
of communication with the deceased
and share their messages
that they receive with others.
And so, as a scientist, I thought,
"There's something to this.
And our science really needs
to take a look at this."
So I know you read goop staffers.
The first was Caitlin.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh, what happened?
[Laura] So I'm just going to be quiet
for one moment.
- Okay.
- We'll see what they have to say. Okay.
Okay, I do have a female figure coming in
on my upper right hand screen.
So that's Mom's side of the family,
it feels very motherly to me.
I'm trying to pull that through
a little bit more. Um...
[stammers]
- Don't feed me.
- Yeah.
- Sorry. Sorry.
- Don't feed the medium.
- I'm trying...
- [laughing] Don't give me anything.
It's my job to work hard
to figure this out,
- is how I want to say it.
- Totally.
You know, like, that's how I get it.
But I'm hearing what sounds like an E-L,
- or an "L" sounding name to me.
- [sobbing] Mm-hmm.
- Is that tied to Mom?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay. It's like I want to hug you
and be like,
"Baby, baby, I'm okay, I'm okay."
This is... she got you here,
and she's so thankful that
you're being so brave to be here.
Do you have artwork from your mom?
- Mm-hmm.
- Like, the real message I want to say,
it's like when you walk in your home,
it's like, boom, you see it right away.
- Do you understand?
- Yeah. That's... [scoffs]
And the way she's saying it to me is like,
"That's my presence in your life.
I am right there every day, honey,
like this.
I've had readings before, so I didn't
anticipate getting so emotional.
I'm also hearing "Happy Birthday."
Is there a birthday coming up
in the family?
- [laughing] Hers.
- Okay, all right.
- It's tomorrow.
- Okay.
[Caitlin] But some of the stuff she said
was really specific,
so it was pretty intense.
So, how does the information come to you?
In order to do the work that I do,
I kind of have to forget that I exist,
in a way, and surrender.
So it's this clearing process
that I just become this vessel
for information to come through,
and then I get information on this screen
that goes on in my mind.
And it will first appear
as a point of light.
So, I'll have a general idea
of who I'm speaking with.
Your grandmother just steps through, too.
They're happy to be reunited,
is how I have to say it,
and they both come through
so loving to you.
Anybody on the sitter's mother's side
of the family
is supposed to come in on my upper right.
Anybody on the sitter's father's side
comes on my lower right,
and then any extended family or friend
or friend of family comes in my middle.
Okay, I don't mean
to get too personal here
but she does show me two children
for you, waiting.
That's how I want to say it.
I guess it's only fair that your mother
can nag you about having kids
- from someplace in the world.
- [laughing]
From the other side,
which is really right here.
She tells me that she came here
as your mom,
but you were the more evolved soul
that taught her so many lessons
about love.
- [sniffling]
- I need to say it that way.
And she's thanking you
for agreeing to be her daughter.
That's how I have to say it.
If you ask for signs and messages,
like, really specific concrete ones
from the other side,
you will get them.
You don't need a psychic medium
to prove it to you.
So wait, are we all psychic?
[Laura] We can all do this,
and I think we all start out intuitive
and we develop our psychic abilities.
And my sense of it is,
as the more you open
and the more you develop,
it's almost like the higher you're able
to perceive
or the louder your volume switch is,
and that kind of highest level
or that highest energy
is being able to perceive consciousness
in spirit form and be a receptor of that.
Wow.
I am so excited for us
to all explore energy today.
Okay. How many of you
have ever felt someone staring at you
and turned and were like,
"Oh, there's that person"?
Okay, that's a sense of directing energy
at somebody.
Energy is real, and there can be
a positive energy exchange
and a negative one.
Now we're about to
play around a little bit
with directing energy at one another.
[Micere] I'm here to take
Laura Lynne Jackson's workshop.
I've worked with a lot of intuitives
and healers for the site at goop.
And she's one of the best mediums
in the world, so it's very cool.
[Laura] One person will be
in the center of the circle,
and we will strike whatever pose
we feel pulled to
to purposely
beam unconditional love
to the person in the center.
Intuition is a mystery to me.
I'm feeling pretty open-minded about it,
but a little unsure of what the outcome's
gonna be.
The person in the center
is just gonna be the receiver.
I'm here today because I've always dabbled
in the medium curiosity, if you will.
I think it's totally real,
something that you can explore,
and I wanted to touch on it
and see what it was all about.
And I'm sure some of you are
already hearing that rational part
of your brain saying, "Energy, what?
None of this stuff's gonna work!"
Just trust it and be open
and see what you experience,
'cause you really
might surprise yourself.
Who would like to volunteer
to be the first one to be beamed?
Ana should do it.
I think it should be Ana, too. Yeah.
- Let's attack her with energy.
- Let's beam you, girl.
- Let's do it.
- For real?
- [man] "Beam me up."
- [woman] I'll beam you up, Ana.
- [laughing]
- I don't really believe
in mediums or psychics.
Either I'm ignorant and I've never been,
like, educated enough on it...
[laughing] I'm, like, about to be tarred
and feathered right now.
...or it's just something that people want
to believe in
because it makes them happy and feel good.
All right,
so everybody get ready and beam.
- [slow-tempo music playing]
- [birds chirping]
[Laura]
Okay, and you can drop your hands.
Did you feel a receiving of energy?
As soon as I stepped in the middle
and everyone put their hands up,
I felt supported.
I literally felt like
I was holding you up.
It was really weird.
- [woman] Levitating you.
- [Laura] Me too.
Because I could feel...
I felt like we were lifting her up.
[laughs] Yeah, I felt like, I was like,
"Am I, like, off the ground?"
Behind my eyelids,
it got brighter and brighter and brighter.
I just felt, like,
a sense of peacefulness.
The energy I felt was above me.
I also felt like I was standing
on almost, like, a hilltop.
[Micere]
When you're in the center of the circle
and you feel everyone
sending their energy to you,
it's just a very loving presence
to have all that non-judgmental attention
put on you.
I don't know, I feel some sort of, like,
guilt for not feeling any of these ways.
- I'm being honest.
- [laughing]
I just don't feel...
I don't feel like I can sympathize
with anything anybody said.
So, our work is gonna try
to get you to feel something
and that's really it, you know?
And that's okay.
You can start from a place
where you're like, "I've got nothing.
I don't know what these other people
are talking about.
How do you feel this?"
That can be a totally great place
to start from.
All I ask of you today is
to just be open to trying.
[Elise] The whole concept
of psychic mediumship
and intuition is unproven,
so it feels silly to believe in it.
Can we prove anything?
I've developed a quintuple blind protocol,
so it's five levels of blinding.
So there's five people involved.
and they're all blinded
to different pieces of information,
so there can't be any sensory leakage.
We'd call you "the sitter,"
the living person wanting to hear from.
So the medium doesn't know anything
about the sitter
or the deceased person.
They have no prior information.
No visual of the person?
No. When the reading takes place,
it's the medium and me on the phone
and all either of us have
is the first name of a deceased person.
And then we do that twice
and then we give you, the sitter,
both readings.
One is for somebody else's
deceased person,
so you're blinded to which one is yours
when you do the scoring.
- Oh, that's pretty cool.
- Hmm.
There's no way anyone can, um, leak...
- unintentionally sensory information.
- [Gwyneth] Right.
And then it needs to be
exceptionally accurate
for the person who's passed that she knows
and exceptionally inaccurate
for the person not connected to her?
[Julie] Right.
Presumably, there are people
who maybe aren't as good at it,
I'm not going to say fraudulent,
but the way in any profession
there are people who are...
- [Julie] It's unregulated.
- Right.
- Yeah.
- You know I'm always saying,
sign me up for whatever research you want.
I'm game.
I want to bring these messages through,
and I want people to help understand this.
Using this quintuple blind protocol,
we have shown that mediums
can report accurate
and specific information
about deceased people
when they aren't using fraud.
They aren't using cold reading
or Googling someone beforehand.
So we can show that certain mediums
- can do that, statistically speaking.
- That's so crazy.
I feel like the quality of your readings
is so interesting, too,
because it's not cold hard facts.
It's like inside jokes, random stories...
Yeah.
- Minutiae.
- Which is why other people can't gauge
whether you got a good reading or not.
We often get people saying,
"You should release the transcripts
of the readings."
That's like releasing transcripts
of your therapy,
like, someone else can't decide.
The only person that can decide
if it was a good reading
is the sitter,
for who the messages were for.
- Totally.
- [Julie] Yeah.
So what else do you teach?
What did you take them through?
We did some activities to help open up
what I call "the four clairs."
We started on doing some exercises
to feel their own energy.
This kind of aura field around us.
And so we started
by drawing the colors we saw.
- That's nuts.
- [Laura] So amazing.
[Shaun] That went into more like
a yellow tone around her shoulders.
That's cool.
And her whole lower body was pink as well.
And then we worked with clairvoyance,
which is "clear-seeing,"
and it's, you know, your mind's eye,
looking without looking.
Oh, wow!
[Laura] You are going to try
to see what is under this,
without seeing it.
Everybody is like, "You're crazy.
I can't do this, that's not a real thing."
And I'm like, "Trust it and try it."
- [Dwi] Whoa!
- So weird.
Another activity we did
is something called psychometry.
The idea there is that
every single object holds energy.
Yeah.
By holding an object,
we can kind of tune into the energy of it,
to use that as almost this cord or link
to the information that's there.
And we had some
extraordinary experiences happen.
[Gwyneth] So cool.
[Laura] Psychic ability is reading energy.
We've been doing that all day.
We're doing it now.
Mediumship is receiving information
from consciousness that is no longer
attached to a physical body,
that has left the physical body.
I'm going to ask you to open up
and use your entire psychic toolbox here...
"the four clairs."
You and your partner will swap objects.
You could just hold it because what
you're doing is you're reading energy.
And I want you to record
any impressions you get from that.
Clairsentience is "clear feeling,"
and that's the on that we're
really embracing
when we try to feel energy of an object.
Now some of our volume switches
are probably at one,
and some are at ten,
and with time and practice,
you can learn how
to turn that up and down.
So you're gonna try to feel anything
and everything you can
from this object.
When you open up all these abilities,
what happens sometimes is that you reach
such an highly open state
that mediumship happens.
Okay, who wants to go first?
I'll volunteer.
[Laura] Okay, what object did you get?
[Ana] Nate gave me a photo.
[Laura] What was the photograph of?
Let's see it.
It's me and my grandfather.
[Laura]
Okay, but we might not know that's you.
It's an elderly gentleman
with a little kid standing on a table.
[laughing]
Okay. Do you know anything
about his grandfather?
His name, his personality, anything
like that prior to seeing the picture?
I don't know anything about Nate's family
besides his daughter.
- [Laura] Let's see what you got.
- [laughs]
Okay. So I said that he was a loving man.
Um, I don't know why I wrote this,
but I wrote that he might have
loved chicken.
- [Ana] Um...
- [laughter]
Is it, like, possible just
to not have this superpower?
[laughs]
[Laura] It's possible to be very much
stuck in your frontal lobe
and to be so distanced from it
that you feel like,
"I can't possibly have this
and this isn't real in the world."
- Unless you have your own experiences...
- But everybody can't have this, right?
We're all born hardwired to each other
and the other side.
This is a gift that belongs to all of us,
but some of us train ourselves
so much out of it
that we don't honor it,
we don't engage in it.
So just stay open to it.
- It's great to...
- I'm open, I'm just waiting...
I'm waiting for the superpower.
- That's why I'm here, yeah.
- And honestly, I would say for you,
don't buy into it until you
have your own experience,
and it becomes your truth,
and then you're like,
"All right, I surrender,
I have to own this now."
And until you do, don't.
I get really scared of my, uh,
intuition sometimes.
Before I had children,
I was much more comfortable with it,
and then my "mother psychosis"
feels sometimes like a premonition,
and it's so terrifying to me.
I've been like, "Oh, my God,
this is a premonition,
something bad's gonna happen."
I have a way to help with that,
because I'm in the same boat as you.
I have three children and believe me,
I do get psychic things for them,
but what I have learned
is when I get information intuitively
for family members, for my kids,
for my role in the world helping others,
it come through with absolutely
- no emotion attached.
- [Gwyneth] Right.
But if it's fear,
then it's your imagination, right?
- [Laura] Then you're projecting it in.
- Right.
Can you share what you got?
- Yeah, so I don't know why...
- What the object was...
[Kelly] It's this awesome dog.
For some reason,
I feel like this was given to you
for a birthday, but it wasn't supposed
to be super sentimental,
but that it, like, became sentimental
from losing what you lost,
which I don't know exactly what that is.
Um, and it also felt like
a very sisterly relationship,
and it was something that was, like,
totally sudden and unavoidable.
Uh, you know, your loss,
it felt very like, kind of like, "What?"
Like, very out of left field. [exhales]
And something with an "M." I don't know.
I kept hearing, like, "M" popping up.
So I don't know if that's, like, a name,
or a city,
or, like, something with an "M."
And I pictured someone
in their, like, 20s,
and there was something to me, like,
either breathing
or allergies or something,
like along, like, a...
I don't know.
Some allergy for some reason?
[Laura] What's interesting,
this picture you're tying
to some loss that happened
that you're saying was sudden
and unavoidable and all of this.
And you've tied it to this picture.
That's interesting.
You got a picture,
and yet you tied it to an event
and a relationship
and so that's very interesting.
So can you share?
- So the "M," that dog's name is Muffin.
- [Kelly] Hmm.
[Dwi] That's her name. Um...
Why, there is, like, the sister.
My brother, who passed away,
gave that to my sister.
And then you're saying, like, you know,
unavoidable or life happening,
and, like, sudden.
Those are all things
that describe his passing.
I don't spend time
with any of these people at work,
barely any time.
I see maybe a few of them in meetings,
Kelly, I've maybe been in two meetings
with her.
And he did paint that,
he was in his 20-somethings...
- Did I say that, too?
- Yeah, he was in his 20s.
Um, and it wasn't supposed
to be a serious gift.
It was just, like, a gift to her
- because she loves the dog so much.
- [Kelly] Right.
Oh, my God.
I was like, "Wow,"
like, physically taken aback.
[Shaun] I mean, Miss Medium over there.
[woman] Congratulations, Kelly,
you are a medium.
Wow!
[Dwi] Kelly mentioned allergy was one
of the first things.
And the story behind that
is my brother was allergic
to dogs and cat fur
so we couldn't get a dog
for the longest time
until we adopted schnauzers.
Those are hypoallergenic dogs.
So I forgot about that,
but that was spot on.
[Laura]
It's a little mind-boggling, right?
'Cause it doesn't fit our paradigm
of like, "Wait a minute..."
Here's this tangible...
Like, how does this make sense?
And yet, you can't deny that.
It's obviously emotional
'cause it's like, who says that? [laughs]
- [Laura] Right.
- So, that's a little weird.
[Laura] I don't think there was
one thing on your list that didn't apply.
You know, the shocking element, of course,
is a bit of that kind of, like,
"Oh, shit, did I just,
like, tap something?"
And then having Dwi validate that,
I thought was, like, insane.
You know, it's always so amazing
to watch that process
and to watch someone discover
for the first time
that they have this ability themselves,
because we all do.
But I've found people who deny
psychic abilities, mediumship,
"That's got to all be,
you know, fraudulent..."
The truth is, this is real.
You know, here's the thing about me.
If I didn't have all these abilities,
if I wasn't a psychic medium,
I think I'd really struggle
believing in it.
And that's why I want everybody
to just experience on his or her own.
We don't just accept something.
Come up with a question or explore an idea
and see where it leads you.
And so I was doing a reading for Ana.
- Oh, really?
- Yes, and she is a little, um...
- Skeptical.
- [Laura] Yes.
[laughing]
- I'm very excited to read for you.
- Excited.
To me this whole...
this whole medium, psychic world
is very much like Santa Claus.
I get it.
It sounds too good to be true, right?
Like,
"Oh, death isn't real in the sense
of your consciousness is still there,
and they watch over us and love us..."
But that's the truth.
Just because something sounds
so fairytale-like and so beautiful,
doesn't mean it's not true.
Okay. First thing I want to say is there...
Are there twins in the family,
or, like, a Gemini birthday?
What is that, June?
No.
I keep seeing, like, two back to back.
- It's very...
- Back to back...
Like, I feel like
I want to talk about twins.
Hmm. I'm trying to think. No.
Okay, I'm going to tell them
to come back to me with that
in another way later...
- Okay.
- ...if that's important, okay?
I do feel like a female figure
coming in on Mom's side of the family,
but I'm like a generation up.
Is there an aunt there that's crossed
or a great aunt for you?
It's like one over.
On my mom's side of the family?
Well, it's my upper right,
which is usually reserved for mom's side.
- That has passed?
- Yes, on the other side.
I have a female figure coming in,
and I feel like it's
your grandmother's sister.
That's how I want to say it.
My grandmother didn't have a sister.
I've had very few experiences
with mediums and psychics,
and I just... I've never had one
where I felt like personally connected.
Your reading's interesting, too,
because I feel like people
are just, like, coming in
who aren't even that connected to you.
- Who I feel like I don't even know.
- Yeah, yeah.
It's one of those things
when you're proving something
that seems, like, outlandish and crazy,
you have to be spot on,
and you have to do it right
if you want to prove your point.
Okay, so it's kind of interesting to me.
Um...
I do feel like on Dad's side
of the family,
grandfather figure there...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...that I want to talk about.
Who in the family crossed very quickly?
I feel like a snap crossing, like...
[sighs] "I'm glad I went this way."
Like, if you can't place it,
don't tell me.
I'm getting my snapping of fingers.
I feel like it was my grandfather
who passed quickly.
- The one we're talking about?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay, 'cause I get this, like...
[snaps fingers]
[Ana] I was hoping that she'd be able
to, like, say things
that were totally me
or totally my situation,
so then I could be like,
"Oh, okay, this is crazy, this is real,
this is whatever it is,"
but I didn't feel that way at all.
Even like some things
that I was like, "Maybe..."
I felt were a little far-fetched.
Is there, like, a funny story
or a picture about a donkey
or is there something with Shrek?
- Mnh-mnh.
- I'm seeing...
Is there anything with, like,
a trip to Mexico?
This is my "psychic charade" part,
and I'm seeing, like, a donkey,
and I'm not sure what I'm supposed
to say about it.
- I'm going to tell him...
- I don't know.
...to come back to me with it
in another way later.
[woman]
Hey, Laura, this is really strange...
I think you're actually reading Lindsay
right now.
- [laughing]
- That can happen.
- This is the problem with...
- [woman] Yeah, that's what I figured.
So, those first people
who came in were yours, right?
- [Lindsay] Yeah, my grandma's a twin.
- [laughing]
- Yeah, I was like, "There are no twins..."
- I'm like, "Who are these people?
'Cause they're not hers,
but they're blasting in."
So this is what happens
when I'm open and they're determined.
And my grandfather passed away
last week,
and I'm getting married
in Mexico next year...
Oh, my God.
I have chills right now.
He loves you so much,
he needed to get that message to you.
- Okay. That's crazy. [laughs]
- That's what happens, you know.
[Laura]
And I love that it got delivered.
My father was just joking
that he really wanted
for the photo booth
at our wedding
in Mexico to have a donkey...
- Stop it right now.
- [Ana] Oh, my God.
[Lindsay] Yeah, and my grandpa laughed
about it
in the hospital days before he passed.
- [Laura] That is so funny. I love this.
- [Ana] Wow.
I was behind the camera, taking notes,
doing my job,
and I looked at my senior producer
and my executive producer,
and I was like kind of
tearing up and freaking out
and was like,
"Oh, my God, she's reading me
while she was reading Ana."
And everybody was kind of like,
"It's a coincidence."
And then once the Mexico thing happened,
I was like, "Okay, that's me."
I mean, it's hard not to be a believer
when all of these things happen.
[Laura] You did exactly the right thing
because you're never supposed
to try and make it fit
or claim it if it's not yours, you know.
But it's always my job just
to deliver the messages,
but sometimes I don't even know.
But it's interesting, too,
when there are a lot of people around,
that will happen. [laughs]
That's so crazy.
Science is just a tool.
It's just one way of knowing,
and intuition is a way of knowing,
but these sort of fringe areas
that go against
accepted mainstream scientific paradigm,
which is consciousness dies
with the body,"
there aren't grants
to look at that kind of stuff.
It's really difficult,
and that's really unfair
that whole group of people
are being categorized
as unethical and fraudulent.
Right.
[Laura]
I've been accused of horrible things,
and I think ultimately,
we have to honor our own truths
and our own purposes.
That's been a journey for my soul,
is to trust in that and own that,
no matter what.
[Ana] I don't feel like
I'm closed off from it.
You can question as much as you want,
but then also, at some point,
you have to be open to change
or new ideas or being educated.
I get why people would
be skeptics and cynics. It's bizarre.
But I don't think there's any harm
into feeling more connected to my mother.
[Laura] The truth that I have come to know
is that consciousness exists outside
of bodily death,
and our lives all intertwine
and interconnect in ways
that are so profound
and so beautiful
that we can't even imagine.
This is a truth I want everyone
to know and embrace.
I think we are all a lot more in tune
with one another
than we think we are.
It's amazing how we can connect
with each other
if we just put in a little more intention
and effort.
[Gwyneth] My last question is...
- who is gonna be president in 2020?
- [laughing]
[Julie] I know.
[theme music playing]