PREVIOUSLY
- What is it?
- It looks like a burn mark.
- You may have missed something.
- You can just see it there.
Goodbye, Dad.
- What are you doing here?
- We fuck. Surely we can be seen together.
And therefore we've donated money so the
museum can build a whole new wing.
- There's only a week left.
- Jeanette has moved in.
But I shouldn't meet her.
Why do I need to be here?
It's not fucking okay!
Not smuggling bags.
Not racing on the forest roads.
It's my son you have in your belly.
- She's just using you.
- She isn't. She loves me.
Was it the first time?
For god's sake, Anna, with Benjamin?
- Anna.
- She had her fun.
She got caught, and now it's over.
- What were you talking to Linn about?
- You, of course.
That you drove your
little sister to suicide.
- The brand marks resemble characters.
- It's the Babylonian number system.
I've thought about
where I'm happy -
- and that's with you.
I love you.
EPISODE 6
There. Now you can go in.
- Hi, Mom!
- Hi, Love.
Hi.
- Did Håkan not pick her up?
- He didn't.
- The school called several times.
- I turned off my phone.
- Where is Håkan?
- He wrote that he went to the summer house.
- I'll call him.
- Don't do that.
A day or two to himself
could be good for him.
And for you.
So you have a chance
to get it together a little.
Mom ... He died.
- Benjamin died.
- Yeah.
But there are many of
us who need you.
THE BRIDGE
There is a connection between the killings
of Helle Anker, Lars-Ove Abrahamsson -
- the attempted murder of
Police Chief Hans Pettersson -
- and the shootings of Aleksander Dover
and Morten Anker.
We ask people to contact us if
they've seen anything.
You already know how
Helle Anker was found.
She sat at a table together with
three dolls: a man and two children.
Hans Pettersson was strung up outside of
the ghost train in an amusement park.
Crucified or like a scarecrow.
There aren't any religious motives.
Lars-Ove Abrahamsson
sat in a beach chair in an empty pool.
- What are the similarities between them?
- I can't comment on the details.
The brand marks in the
victims' mouths were numbers.
The Babylonian number system.
It's 3500 years old.
It's a base-60 number system.
There's no character for zero.
The code on Morten Anker's refrigerator.
Sorry. Visitor.
Hi.
I think I know something about
the murders you're investigating.
Well?
I saw the press conference on tv.
The first one ... Helle ...
- Helle Anker.
- Yeah. I saw the photos on the internet.
It made me think of a Dutch
painter named Waarheid.
It's a pseudonym that means
'truth' in Dutch.
- Why are we talking about him?
- He made a piece.
There's a room with a man -
- and around him hang marionettes
of women and children.
- What's the point?
- Sorry.
The point is, the piece is
called 'The Perfect Family'.
- That means ...
- We understand what it means.
There's also another piece
called 'The Nightmare'.
It's a scarecrow in a
big pile of birdseed -
- which is surrounded by dead birds
that didn't dare to eat anything.
Keep going. It's fine.
Frank Nielsen painted
'A Day at the Beach'.
It's an abstract painting,
but that's what it's called.
Do you understand what I'm thinking?
You think that some of the murders
are inspired by the titles of the artwork.
Yes.
Every crime in the world
could be named after works of art.
If you have a dead person
who has a little smile on -
- you could call that 'Mona Lisa'.
- Sure, it ...
- In principle, you could do that.
Thanks so much for coming.
It's always good to get some tips.
- Do the pieces have anything in common?
- No, they don't.
But they all belong to Freddie Holst and are
on exhibition at the museum where I work.
We want to see that exhibition.
Now. Immediately.
- You're not allergic, are you?
- No.
Thanks.
Hi.
I'm Jeanette.
- Is the kitchen in the guest house broken?
- It's nicer with company.
I can make sure that someone
from the staff eats down there.
- I think I'll go.
- No, you stay here.
You may come and go as you please.
I apologize on my wife's behalf.
I'm going.
What the hell is going on with you?
You're going to listen to the radio now?
Honestly, Åsa.
The silent treatment?
What are you, twelve years old?
And Swedish radio ...
What a mess.
How long did you follow
Anna Ekdahl to get the photos?
I got a tip that she was in Copenhagen.
I wish I'd never gotten it.
I'm getting death threats on the internet.
- Twitter is like a hate competition.
- Tina, he died. Benjamin, he died.
- And how exactly is that my fault?
- You took the photos.
Tina.
Cross your fingers for me.
Here we have 'A Day at the Beach',
Frank Nielsen.
It's said that the artist placed
four animals in the painting -
- but I can't see them.
- How many pieces do you have here?
- 32.
Do you know the names of all of them?
Can you make a list?
- Now.
- Of course.
Do you think there's anything to this?
- It's the best we have right now.
- So Holst, too.
And you think this has something
to do with my art?
- Maybe.
- You don't know any of those people?
I've never seen them,
never heard about them.
Is there anyone who's threatened you?
- Do you know what I do?
- Not in detail.
I make companies profitable.
- By firing people?
- Yeah, sometimes.
Sometimes I restructure the
company, downsize, outsource.
I do what's necessary and don't let
emotions get in the way.
- Not everyone appreciated it.
- My father didn't appreciate it.
- Did I buy your father's business?
- No, not you. Someone like you.
- Ah, someone like me.
- Yeah.
We want a list of the businesses
you have worked with in the last few years.
Of course, but it's quite a few
and still a little far-fetched.
Does this mean anything to you?
It's the account number of
my secret account in Switzerland.
No, I'm joking with you.
I don't have any accounts in Switzerland.
Sorry. He's pressing on my
bladder all the time.
It doesn't matter.
I like looking at you.
- Claes ...
- Can't I say that you're beautiful?
- Pregnancy suits you.
- Thanks.
It's so nice to see
how well you're doing.
- It's been going well for a while.
- I know. I read about you.
I follow you on Facebook.
Do you feel uncomfortable
with me and Freddie?
I would be lying if I said
that it didn't give me a little pain -
- but the important thing is
that you're happy.
- Are you happy?
- What kind of question is that?
It's a question we should ask ourselves
and our loved ones more often.
Yes, I'm happy.
- Okay. Have you heard my talks?
- No.
I have a talk tomorrow in Malmo
if you want to come and listen.
We'll see. Maybe.
- Thanks for lunch, and for the company.
- It was really nice.
- Fucking hell.
- She's only going to hurt you again.
She let you down once. She's having
children with the guy who crushed you.
Why are you seeing her at all?
Wait a minute. Everything about
you has been strange -
- but this crosses the fucking line.
- Sorry, but someone has to ...
- No, you don't need to do anything.
I felt flattered by your attention,
but this ...
- Out of the car. Out! Out!
- We're in Denmark.
You came here, so you can
get back. Out of the car.
Out, for fuck's sake! Close the door!
John checked up on Claes Sandberg,
Freddie Holst's former partner.
- Why former?
- He had alcohol problems.
Holst sent him to rehab.
So Holst could take care of the business -
- he took over Sandberg's part. When
he got full control, he sold it.
- Nice guy, huh?
- Sandberg got less than half.
He also lost the art he'd
bought with his wife.
Three years later, Holst also married
Åsa, Claes Sandberg's ex-wife.
Bring him in for questioning.
I understand that you're skeptical,
but it was for the best that it happened.
It took several years to realize it,
and yes, I hated Freddie -
- I admit it.
But happiness is a choice.
- He stole your joint business.
- No.
He stole a portion of the
profits from the sale.
- You lost all your art.
- Yes, among other things.
- And your wife.
- He didn't steal her. She left me.
- She left you for him.
- She would have left me anyway.
You have to understand
what state I was in.
I was deeply unhappy. I made
Åsa unhappy, and I drank.
When Freddie betrayed me, I had
to realize what was important in life.
- So you chose happiness.
- Yeah.
But like I said, it took time.
Are you happy?
- Who, me?
- Yes.
Are you serious?
- Are you happy?
- Define happiness.
Happiness is a lasting
feeling of well-being
- that is independent of external
circumstances, positive or negative.
Okay. You know what, Jesus?
I think the interview is over.
- Do you like it?
- Sorry. I was just curious.
It's okay. Of course you
can see the nursery.
We've done everything so
that he'll lack nothing.
Yeah. I can see that.
Here.
Only for Marc.
Yeah.
- Is there anything wrong?
- No.
It's stupid, but ...
I'd imagined that my child
would have a green room.
- It's not your child.
- No, of course.
I didn't mean it that way.
But I agree with you that green
is better. And now it's two against one.
Is he kicking?
- No. I think he's sleeping.
- May I feel anyway?
Um ... Yeah. Of course.
Oh!
The search at Sandberg's place
didn't yield anything. Let him go.
- Have we checked his alibi?
- Of course.
The night Helle Anker was killed,
he was in Varberg.
When Morten Anker was shot, he was
in Borås. There's no link to the victims.
Do we really believe all that about
Holst? All we have are the titles of the art.
- It's too early to write him off.
- Especially now.
What is it?
The list of companies Holst
has done business with.
- Number four from the bottom.
- Andersen TL.
- Are you coming?
- Yeah.
- What were you reading?
- When?
Yesterday. When I came. You said
you were reading something or other.
Why do you want to know that?
It hit me that we have sex, but
I don't know anything about you.
- That's the way I want it.
- Why?
Everyone I've been close to
has left me and/or hurt me.
Okay.
'Psychology: The Science of Mind
and Behavior', Nigel Holt.
A year ago, we needed capital
and so Freddie Holst came in.
Wasn't it you who started the business?
And then he took control?
Yeah, but it was either that
or bankruptcy. We were lucky.
Does it have to do with the murders?
Why are we talking about Freddie?
Has he made major changes
since he arrived?
Saga, just continue.
I'll be there in a minute.
Has he?
Many of the things from the
crime scene are in the catalog.
- And that helps us how?
- The order form on the back is missing.
- What did he say in there?
- Eight were fired. Two were warned.
He stopped working with
two suppliers.
So at least ten have reason to dislike Holst.
- Why don't you like him?
- I don't like his type.
- What's his type?
- He's one of those who are raking it in.
Making money in a capitalist economy
is probably not that bad.
Can I not get permission to
dislike the man?
Sure.
- There are people you don't like.
- No, not without reason.
Hi. Rasmus Larsson.
It's good you could come.
- It's regarding the threat.
- What threat?
Then I must have misunderstood.
Saga was at my place last night.
It was very unpleasant.
I'd like to hear more about that.
But first I want to discuss
the investigation and trial -
- which led to you lose custody
of your other daughter, Jennifer.
332-3948 ...
And 337-3951 ...
And finally there's a fire truck.
112-9833.
And when was that?
Yeah, good.
And where was that sent to?
There was one order with all the things. It
was sent to a postbox in Malmo in August.
And you know whose postbox it is?
I don't understand ...
Toys from the crime scenes were sent to
your business. You don't understand that?
Sure, sure, but to whom?
Those you dismissed, they were
still here in August, weren't they?
Yes. They were dismissed,
but they continued until September 1st.
We need a list of employees, as well
as terminations and warnings.
Of course.
Who empties your postbox?
Usually it's Kjell Söder.
He was the first at work the morning
after Helle Anker was killed.
- Is he working today?
- No, he quit.
He was going to travel.
- When did he stop working?
- About a week ago.
That day you were at the business,
that was his last day.
- The newspaper ended our collaboration.
- That's what Matilda said.
Is it worse to take photos
than to publish them?
It's not, but Matilda needs
to make it look that way.
I've called around.
I can't get work.
- What should I do?
- You can buy my photos.
Tina! I can't do that.
You're screwed.
I'm sorry. Really.
[Hidden number]
Anna Ekdahl (Eurovision 1996)
is in Copenhagen with her lover ...
- Hello, it's John.
- Hi, John.
- It's Tina.
- I can hear that. Thanks for last time.
Can you help me with
a phone number?
I've received threats.
What was Rasmus Larsson doing here?
Don't you know what he's done?
Everyone makes mistakes, Saga.
He is aware of it.
He put the whole case at stake.
- After that episode.
- It wasn't an incident. It was an infraction.
Please stop interrupting me.
After that episode, Rasmus worked for
me and did exemplary work.
- Everybody deserves a second chance.
- So he should work with us now?
- No, he's helping me with something else.
- What?
- Do we still have nothing after that press conference?
- No, not yet.
And what about Kjell Söder?
No previous convictions,
no connection to the victims.
I had hoped that we would be
closer to solving this. Don't you agree?
I don't know how much
closer you were hoping for.
Let me say that I had
higher expectations.
I know something about the murders.
Can we meet? 6:45. Come alone or I'll
go. Reply when you're there.
Arrived
- Saga Norén, Malmo Police.
- Saga, it's Lillian.
- Hans is on a respirator.
- Did he stop breathing?
Yes, all of a sudden. They've done
tests, but they don't know what it is.
- His autonomic nervous system isn't working.
- Yes, but they don't know why.
- I don't either.
- No, that's clear.
I thought you'd want to know.
Yes, I would. Thanks.
What's up, turtle doves? John,
did Saga say where she was going?
No.
- I'm going to step out and call her.
- You do that.
Did you look up that hidden number
that I asked you about?
I don't normally do this, but
when you've received threats ...
Her name is Eva Rosenqvist.
She has three numbers.
Do you know her?
No, I'm just surprised.
It's usually guys
do these things.
Hey, you. I'm out with
John and Tina.
We're having a beer.
Do you want to come?
- No, I don't like beer.
- You and I could just do something else.
- No, I want to be alone.
- Not even a little sex?
- No.
- Okay.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah.
It was him. It was the boyfriend.
Benjamin.
The number I got a tip about Anna
from belongs to Benjamin's mother -
- but I've checked, and
it's his phone.
- Why would he give you a tip?
- To make Anna's husband jealous.
His plan backfired.
But he wanted the photos to be
published, and people must know.
You cannot blame a dead teenager.
Should everyone living with his suicide
know that he was responsible as well?
- Now everyone thinks it was my fault.
- You'd be giving a dead boy the blame.
It won't make your situation better.
Just worse for everyone else.
- Hi. Eva Rosenqvist?
- Yes.
I want to talk ...
It wasn't my fault
that your son died.
What? Did you know Benjamin?
No, I'm ... I'm a photographer,
and he ...
He tipped me off about an address
that I should ...
What do you mean,
it wasn't your fault?
Nothing.
- I'm so sorry.
- Wait.
Who are you?
Wait! Who the fuck are you?
Hey there.
- Who found him?
- The cleaning woman over there.
Make sure she stays here.
I want to talk to her.
She's pretty shaken up,
but that's understandable.
- Hit the cat out of the barrel ...
- What is that?
Hit the cat out of the barrel is a game
played in Denmark for Shrovetide.
You have a barrel with a cat inside.
The children hit it with clubs until it breaks.
- Out falls a bunch of candy.
- Like a piñata.
Yeah.
Why is there a cat inside?
In the old days, there was
a living cat in the barrel.
- Why is that?
- I don't know.
What happens when that hits zero?
We found this in his pants.
Håkan Ekdahl.
- When did you see him last?
- The night before last. He was at Anna's.
- We want to talk to your daughter.
- Is that really necessary?
Yes.
She's in the bedroom.
She's taken something to calm her.
Be careful. She's very
fragile right now.
- Then perhaps you should talk to her.
- Why is that?
Linn says that this sort of interaction
with other people isn't my strong side.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Why didn't your daughter report
him missing if he was gone?
He had written that he
went to the summer house.
We thought that he
wanted a little time to himself.
Why did you think that?
Anna was unfaithful to Håkan.
He had just found out.
Who was she unfaithful with?
A young man. But he's also dead.
He committed suicide. There ...
A lot has happened.
We need the address
to the summer house.
A gymnasium. A man
was killed with a wooden club.
A Danish game called
'Hit the Cat Out of the Barrel' -
- and a clock that counts down.
Does that mean anything to you?
No, I don't know ...
Yes, the clock that counts down.
There is a piece of Eduardo Paolazzi's
called 'Countdown to Disappointment'.
- That means ...
- I know English. Is it hanging in the museum?
No, it's hanging at Holst's house.
How do you know that?
We were there to pick
up the other artwork.
Thanks.
- That strengthens the connection to Holst.
- Yeah.
Thanks.
- Sorry, what are you doing here?
- We're going to paint.
- I don't think so. It was just painted.
- It was us who did it.
- But now it will also be green.
- Green?
- Who said that?
- Freddie ... He called yesterday.
Hi!
Oh, I've missed you.
Are you okay?
Can you stand being here?
Freddie's fine. It's just his wife.
She doesn't like me.
But it's okay. What are you up to?
- Making some plans for the house.
- I'm so looking forward to it.
Are you okay, Jeanette?
I don't want you here, Marc.
It makes Jeanette restless.
And she needs peace and quiet.
Do you think she seemed
restless and upset?
Jeanette is my girlfriend, so you
must live with my being here.
You'll get 30,000 if you keep away.
Are you taking the piss?
That's the maximum. A few weeks.
Buy something that can numb the pain
or otherwise entertain you.
- 40,000.
- 30.
I subtract 1000 for every word you say.
So we're down to 28,000.
Nod if you agree.
Come on.
Hi.
Police.
Saga Norén, Malmo Police.
- What do you want?
- Have you seen this man?
- Yeah, that's Håkan. Isn't he here?
- No.
- His car is parked over there.
- I'll call the technicians.
He was here yesterday.
I saw that he had a visitor.
The car was in the driveway.
- What kind of car was it?
- No idea.
- It was yellow, anyway.
- Thanks.
- Kjell Söder's car is yellow.
- Yeah.
Kjell Söder. Do we know where he is?
He didn't leave anything behind.
He had a ticket to Singapore on the 8th.
- Do we know if he took the flight?
- Not yet.
- Connections to the victims?
- No.
- Hi there.
- What are you doing here?
I was passing by and thought
that you would want to see this.
The brand mark on the
victim in the gymnasium.
- It's a four.
- So that's the whole code, then.
If he has a number or character for
each victim, we have three to go.
Maybe.
The cause of death was blunt
force to the head and body.
I can't say how many hits
he got, but it was many.
He had an extra penis in his underwear.
It will be DNA-examined, but I
think it's Lars-Ove Abrahamsson's.
What about Håkan?
Was he missing any body parts?
Two. Both eyes were taken.
Was there anything else?
- Not unless you have questions.
- No.
Helle Anker, heart.
Hans, hand.
Lars-Ove Abrahamsson, penis.
Håkan Ekdahl, eyes.
The body parts seem to have another
function besides being trophies.
We've touched on symbolism before.
So Helle Anker, she's heartless.
What about Hans and the hand?
The long arm of the law.
Yeah, if there's anyone who still
calls the police that today.
Lars-Ove Abrahamsson, abuse.
What about Håkan Ekdahl?
Something he saw.
Something he should have seen, perhaps.
What about the artwork?
- Do the victims have a connection to Holst?
- No.
It's there. We just haven't found it.
- What were the workers doing here?
- You know why.
- I don't know why.
- I want another color.
- Right after she moved in?
- Yes, we've talked about it.
She shouldn't be in there.
What does she have to do with the color?
- I thought it was boring.
- So my choice was boring.
Yeah, it was fucking boring, Åsa.
It was unimaginative.
Okay. Is there anything else she'll do?
Does she like the furniture?
- What about the car? Are my clothes okay?
- Shut up, Åsa.
- I will not shut up.
- Shut up now, I say.
It'll be okay.
- Hi. What's your name?
- Emelie.
Emelie. How are you?
Or wait. Now we'll see.
Answer when I flip. Ready?
- One, two, three.
- Good.
'Good'!
Am I a mind reader? No.
Or is it that people who come to
my talks actually have it good?
No. It's not like that.
The question is usually not sincere.
It's a kind of rhetorical agreement.
I want to hear 'good' -
- and that's what I get.
Hi. Welcome.
But try again to answer:
"I'm not doing so well today.
I'm not actually particularly
happy right now."
How would that feel?
Would it be hard? A little embarrassing?
People don't really want to
listen to my problems.
There's another alternative.
Say 'good' and mean it.
- Did you not understand what I said?
- Do you want to hear something?
No, you should just go now.
Blue marks and other signs of violence
can show up several hours after death.
If the victim isn't autopsied,
it might never be discovered.
Your dad had blue marks on the sides
of his nose. Bleeding on the upper lip.
It's damage that may occur
if you're being strangled.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I called the nursing home. You were
alone with him when he died.
But don't worry. I painted over it.
You can even have an open
casket if you want.
You can thank me by taking
me to dinner tonight.
Two minutes. Get rid of her.
I'll wait in the car.
Annika ...
Hi. Nice of you to come.
Thanks. It was interesting.
- A little vague for me ...
- Vague?
A little unscientific, maybe.
I'm the proof that it actually works.
I don't really know what you mean.
- Shall we go some place else?
- Yeah, no ...
I can't.
- Your girlfriend?
- No, she's nothing like that.
I actually came over to
Sweden for your sake.
I have some meetings.
I didn't think you'd come.
We'll do it another time. Okay?
Bye.
5000.
Are you in?
3200. And this.
I have bad news.
- Did something happen with Hans?
- No.
But they found your mother dead.
It seems to be suicide.
How?
She was found in her car in the
garage with the motor running.
I know that you've had
a strained relationship.
What did she say?
You've lost both your parents in
a short period. It must affect you.
I don't know how yet.
Tell me what you want to do.
If you want some downtime.
- Take some time off.
- I don't want that.
Thanks.
I hope that you can hear this,
even if you've gotten worse.
Now my mom has killed herself, too.
Just like my sister, Jennifer.
I thought we were doing well,
Jennifer and I.
But then ...
She said that she was going to a friend's
house, but threw herself in front of a train.
Yesterday we questioned a man
who defined happiness.
I didn't recognize what he described
because I had never experienced it.
Maybe that's why I
couldn't save Jennifer.
I couldn't see that
she wasn't happy.
I'm sorry. You need to go. It's late.
I'm not disturbing him. It's good for him
if there's someone speaking to him.
It's 11:00. Visiting hours are over.
- Saga?
- Can I come in?
- You want to come in?
- Yes.
We can easily go somewhere
else that's open.
Why can't I just come in?
It's really late.
It's just as late if
we go somewhere else.
Okay.
Why haven't you gotten rid
of their things?
It's six years ago that they disappeared.
Yeah. It feels like giving up
if I throw them out.
If their things are here -
- it's like they can
still come back again.
- That's irrational thinking.
- Yeah, I know that.
But I'm not particularly rational
when it comes to them.
Not at all, actually.
Did something or other happen ...
Why did you come?
My mom killed herself.
I was with Hans, but they kicked me out.
Instead of going home I came here.
Saga ...
You haven't thrown out anything.
If they came back, they will have
outgrown the clothes and toys.
They're not coming back. I know that.
Up there.
It's just ... It's the rest of me
that has trouble realizing it.
I need to find out what
happened to them.
That's why you got
the investigation.
So you're alone a lot.
At home, you mean?
Yeah. Or ...
I see them. Alice and the girls.
They're here in the house
with me. All the time.
I talk to them,
and they talk to me.
- Are they here now?
- Only Alice.
The girls, they're sleeping.
In there.
Where is she?
There.
- She talks to you?
- Yeah.
- But you already know what she'll say?
When we have sex, is it like
you're being unfaithful?
No.
No, it's okay.
If we had sex here, would she see?
We're not going to have sex here. But
you're very welcome to stay and sleep.
Move over.
Do you want something to help you sleep?
No. I can always sleep.
- Goodnight.
Do you want a job?
Documents. Good money.
Tell me more.
Send an email to
L369G42@russmail.com
English subtitles by S.E.
kyckling@protonmail.com