Previously
The victim's name is Helle Anker.
Married and has a son with Natalie Anker -
- and from a previous marriage,
Morten Anker.
I didn't touch her!
What is your family life like?
Small talk.
The two of us are only going to
work together. Nothing else.
I know that you don't want to see me.
Saga, Dad is dying!
Jennifer is gone.
It's only us two left.
- The money is gone.
- Do you think I've taken it?
I'm going to run away.
They'll kill me if I stay here.
Helle Anker was a modern, lesbian woman
who would destroy the nuclear family -
- and I hope that her death also means -
- that her crazy ideas are buried with her.
Hope it's nice.
- So let's go to your place.
- Okay.
She lived in Valby. She's a store
manager, or works in an office.
See if you can get a little sleep.
So now you need someone new over there.
So take me.
Read up on the case, get ready
and contact Saga Norén.
EPISODE 2
There were many reactions to your post
about Helle Anker's death.
- Yes, and many were positive.
So you maintain that you
are glad that she died?
I said I'm happy that we'll avoid
meaningless experiments with children
Can't it be that you're inspiring
people to 'solve' the problem?
Should we abolish free speech because
some can't interpret what we say?
- No, that isn't what I'm saying.
- Of course that's what you're saying.
We're going to see a clip
that you put out during the week.
Do you think it's too much to ask
that our church have a clear message?
And that that message is based on God's word?
I don't think so.
I have nothing against homosexuals.
You know that.
Of course they should have the same
legal rights as the rest of us.
But why should they get
married in the church?
That question I ask you,
Fabian Christensen.
I now declare you
to be a married couple -
- to both God and man.
You are a priest and a prominent
advocate for gay marriage.
I don't understand how
you can be both.
And why the church hasn't thrown you out.
The Bible is unambiguous.
If you had been Christian,
which I doubt that you are,
- and a priest when it was written -
- you would have been stoned to death.
And they say that it wasn't
better in the past.
So you see no problem in that
it can be perceived as encouraging?
Do you see a problem
in that I am expressing an opinion -
- that may not be politically correct,
but that is in no way illegal?
You need to work a little on your
wording, because it sounds like it.
The Bridge
- Who are you?
- Henrik Saboe, Copenhagen Police. Who are you?
- Lars Andersen, Director.
I just wanted to examine how much
needed to be done before it can drive again.
Your colleague said that
you were finished here.
So we had.
She asked who was here first
that morning, after it happened.
- Who asked about it?
- Your Swedish colleague.
I've found out who it was.
Kjell Söder was first on the site.
- Kjell Söder? Is he here now?
- Yes, he is.
I'm probably driving directly from here,
but we can talk about it later.
I have to run. Kisses.
Saga, come with me.
How are you?
I broke the rules when
I took my weapon home.
- Yes, but how are you?
- Good.
The thing with Hanne
was a traumatic experience.
When you were there, you felt
that you bore a part of the blame.
You were right in that I couldn't
know it. Morten is paranoid -
- that he would put a bomb in the
trailer was impossible to predict.
It can still affect you.
Not so much that I can't do my job.
No, but something is wrong.
I can see it.
If you don't want to say anything, I must
send you home, whether you like it or not.
My mother is here.
Your mother? I have never heard
you talk about your mother.
I don't. We don't see each other.
I haven't seen her in 20 years.
So what does she want now?
My father is dying.
She wants me to visit him.
And you don't want to.
No, they aren't good for me.
It was I who broke contact.
Is there anything you want to talk about?
Anything that I can help with?
No.
If there is anything, you know
where you can find me.
Yeah. Here or in your new
apartment in Copenhagen.
Exactly.
You don't like it, but I think
you need a hug.
Ah.
Henrik Saboe, Copenhagen Police.
Lillian has sent me.
Hi. Welcome. Hans Pettersson.
I'm Lillian's husband
and the boss on the Swedish side.
This is Saga.
She's leading the investigation.
- May I work now?
- Yes.
Morten Anker, 27. Son of
Helle Anker and Villy Bartram.
The father died in 2003.
After basic training, goes to
Helmand Province in Afghanistan.
He's been there three times.
Got into trouble on the last.
How?
He was part of a group that was
accused of rape by a woman in town.
He and two others were
abducted and tortured.
Post-traumatic stress disorder.
He left the army and lives
off a modest pension.
One hasn't heard much from
him these last years.
- What about the surveillance cameras?
- I've gotten the videos.
If one watches the 15 minutes before
the perpetrator turns off the cameras -
- way too many cars go by.
- What's this about cameras?
- Between the murder scene
and where she was found.
- Do we know that was his route?
- No, but it's likely.
He had luggage. Start with vans
and station wagons and locate the owners.
The first who arrived at
Andersen TL was Kjell Söder.
He came at 5:20 A.M.
At the time it wasn't locked.
- How do you know that?
- I've just been there.
I met the director. The security company
was last there at 3:47 A.M.
- You know that already.
The killer must have come after that.
The cameras were shut off at 5:10 A.M.
Now they know how she was found.
Those who found her took pictures.
- 'The Clown Murder'.
- That's not correct.
The drawings on the faces are emoticons.
- Yes, but now they call it that.
- But it's wrong.
They're finished at Morten Anker's place.
There are no more bombs. Saga.
I can ask someone else
to go with Henrik if you want.
- Why?
- Because of what happened.
No, that's not necessary.
You just have to follow.
Don't wait for an invitation.
So you and your boss hug.
He thought that non-erotic
contact would comfort me.
- Do you need comforting?
- No.
- Great car.
- That's what people say.
You may not drive it.
- Have you read the case file?
- Yeah, I've done that at least.
- It's not so big yet.
- So you have no questions.
It was you who put Martin in,
wasn't it?
If you mean reported, that was me.
I had to ask.
I know that Martin suffered.
I thought you were friends.
We are. Or were, at least.
It must have been hard for you.
With Martin and colleagues after.
We have a legal system.
One cannot be above it.
What are you doing?
I'm making kind of a map of the area.
We've photographed it.
I know that.
Are you okay?
We don't have to both be inside.
You can wait here if it's difficult.
- I don't know how thorough you are.
- I'm very thorough.
That doesn't mean that your
self-image agrees with reality.
True, but I believe it.
Ah.
Didn't Helle get a typewritten,
threatening letter?
- Do you hunt?
- Why do you ask?
Can this be a deer heart?
I don't know.
- It looks like a human heart.
- It's a little large, no?
It must be from a fawn or something.
Come and see this.
Anti-depressants. Anxiolytic.
They're issued by the same doctor.
Marianne Givskov.
- Marianne!
- Morten?
- I need my medicine.
- I couldn't stop him.
- Sit down.
- I need my medicine.
- Yeah. Sit down. Sit down, Morten,
and we'll figure it out. What happened?
- I didn't touch her.
- Who are you talking about?
- Morten?
- My mother. I didn't touch her.
- I must have my pills right now.
I don't have them here, but we
can go out together and find them.
Lie down and rest a little while,
and then we can talk about it.
Sorry. Now look. Here they are.
Shall we go back together?
Morten. Morten!
Out of the way
Morten has no car.
Put up wanted posters of him on
all public transportation.
- Yeah. We'll put out a canine patrol.
Make sure. And put up wanted
posters in both countries.
- Are you always so bossy?
- I'm not bossy. I'm efficient.
I understand if you're not
used to that in Denmark.
- Who texts you all the time?
- That's private.
You're doing it during work hours.
Her name's Line.
I met her at a museum yesterday.
You were lucky. Only 2% of people meet
their future partners in public places.
I don't think I'd call her my future partner.
Anyway, I'm about to end it right ... now.
Why do you know things like
percentages, and who meets where?
I read a lot.
But this doesn't really count.
It was arranged beforehand.
I'm in a singles club.
When they organize a museum visit,
you get a little sticker.
So you can see
who else is a member.
So you go over and talk
with the other members, and ...
Do you have sex?
Such a cumbersome arrangement
should at least result in sex.
Do you think I'm one
of your girlfriends?
I don't have any girlfriends.
Do you have sex?
- Yeah.
Just go up. I'll be there in a minute.
Stop following me, or I'll report you.
Saga, you lost a sister, and we
lost a daughter. We need to talk about it.
Jennifer never recovered -
- after she was psychologically
and physically abused for years.
So she committed suicide.
There, now we've talked about it.
So you still think it was my fault.
I know that it was your fault!
- What is that?
- Jennifer's journals. Read them.
- Why?
- So you can see that you were wrong.
and so you can visit Dad
and be reconciled.
Reconciliation requires that
both partners want it, and I don't!
In that case, your colleagues
might be interested.
In everything you've done to us.
No, sorry, Saga.
I didn't mean to threaten you.
It wasn't.
We're proud of you.
We read about you ... Can you look
at me when I'm speaking to you?
Read this. That's all I ask.
- Who was that?
It was my mom, and I don't want
to talk about it, if that's what you're thinking of doing.
Check this.
It's from Morten Anker's refrigerator.
- What is it?
- That's what I want to know.
The dogs lost the trail, but the
wanted posters are out.
Good.
It gives no hits on Google.
- What's that?
- Journals.
- Connected to the case?
- No.
Saga Norén, Malmo Police. I have
something for Forensics in Lund.
We've found a new body.
Do we know who it is?
His name is Fabian Christensen.
A 60-year-old priest from Copenhagen.
Was he reported missing?
No. He texted his wife that he would
be coming home at the usual time.
- Is there a connection to Helle Anker?
- Not as far as we know.
The heart is still there.
He might be missing something else.
That car there, is it his?
Yes, that's the victim's.
Why are they smiling like that?
It's a smiley. On electronic communications,
it shows that something should be seen as a joke.
Thanks for that, Wikipedia, but do you think
the perpetrator sees the killings as a joke?
No, it's not likely.
So why are they smiling like that?
We were going out tonight ...
to the theatre and to eat afterwards.
Do you know who could have done it?
We had our wedding 14 days ago -
- but we had no time to celebrate.
- So he hadn't received threats.
- I should cancel the table.
I can do that for you if you
tell me the name of the restaurant.
- Geranium.
I'll do that, and you just answer
my colleague's questions. Okay?
What do you want to know?
If your husband had received threats.
Yes. There were a couple of unpleasant -
- letters and emails.
He was the first priest in Denmark
who married same sex couples.
- Did he keep any of them?
- No, he deleted all of them.
This came this morning.
He never had a chance to see it.
A threatening letter. Typewritten.
I've cancelled the table at Geranium.
Elise ...
Did your husband know a Helle Anker
or Morten Anker?
The name seems familiar, but that's
because of that crazy woman ...
- Which crazy woman?
- On the internet.
- Lise Friise Andersen.
- Go ahead and sit down.
- Thanks.
Several students saw Karen
go up to Molly and hit her.
- Good. Then word spreads quickly.
- Where did you hit?
The nose first, and then
the side of her eye.
This is completely unacceptable. We have
zero tolerance for violence in this school.
And also for bullying.
How did that go last time?
Is this what you teach her?
That violence is a solution?
I teach her not to be afraid.
Now it's up to you whether this
will be repeated. Come, Sweetie.
- Hello?
- Yeah, hi, it's me.
- Where did you get my number?
- I asked Samira.
Things went badly yesterday.
Also, I haven't taken the money.
I was a little angry, but mostly upset
that you could possibly believe that.
But I want to help you.
Can we not meet and talk about it?
We need to find a solution.
It's eating me up.
Where are you?
I can come out to you.
- It's better if we meet in the city.
- Okay. Where and when?
The subscriber cannot answer your
call. Leave a message after the tone.
The police have been here.
We need to meet.
The Bible is unambiguous.
If you had been Christian, which
I doubt, and you were a priest
- at the time it was written,
you would have been stoned to death.
And they say it wasn't better
in the past.
Lise Friis Andersen.
She was also against Helle Anker.
She seemed happy after her death.
- How do you know that?
- She was on a Danish tv program.
- About freedom of expression.
- Could she have done it?
She could have also
just encouraged it.
- How is it going with Morten Anker?
- There isn't anyone who's seen him.
- What about the thing from the refrigerator?
- It could be a personal code.
What about the meat and the typewriter?
The heart was from a deer.
The blood was from animals.
- And the typewriter?
- There is nothing new yet.
The last ribbon they compared must
be 20 years old.
So we only have her.
I just don't understand
why you're here.
Two people you have spoken
negatively about have been killed.
- Two? Who other than Helle Anker?
- Fabian Christensen.
- What? That's terrible. But
it doesn't explain why you're here.
I told you. Two people whom you
have spoken negatively about are dead.
There must be other people
who have spoken negatively about them.
They were public figures.
Is there anyone who has shown
excessive interest in your opinions?
- Excessive interest?
- Yeah.
No one has shown excessive interest.
There are many who have shown interest -
- but you can read that for yourself.
So you haven't gotten any
mail or phone calls.
- From people who murder in my name?
- Has anyone written by typewriter?
Most of my followers
live in the 21st century.
So you don't own
a typewriter yourself.
- No.
- Do you know Morten Anker?
- Is he related to Helle Anker?
He's her son.
There is nothing that I put out
that calls for violence.
- That's debatable.
- I am a trained lawyer, so no, it can't be.
I express my opinions and I cannot
be responsible for what my followers do.
Should we warn the people
she's spoken badly of?
We can't do that without risking
being accused of defamation.
The killings happened directly after her posts.
- That doesn't mean anything.
- And she's married to Lars Andersen.
- How do you know that?
- The wedding photo up there.
- Let's take a closer look at the couple.
- Now.
- Or first thing in the morning.
- Why not now?
I thought that we should go
eat dinner together. At Geranium.
I never cancelled the
Christiansens' reservation.
- Why didn't you do that?
- It's impossible to get a table there.
- No, I don't want to.
- Okay. Is there a reason,
or should I just feel crushed?
I have a meeting in Lund,
and so I'm going to work.
- So we'll just do it another time.
- I don't care for that sort of activity.
She's very different. I think
she has some diagnosis or other.
- You wouldn't like her.
- Why not?
I don't know. She's very ...
She's very honest.
Like totally without boundaries.
And so she doesn't have any walls.
I want to talk to her.
I want to see if I can get her to help me.
How?
I'll just get to know her better first.
I invited her to come with
me to Geranium tonight.
I had gotten a table,
but she didn't want to. So I gave up.
So it's just you and me tonight. Quiet.
Nice.
Hi.
- Have you found anything?
- On the bodies or the journal you sent me?
Both. Let's start with the bodies.
- Go ahead.
- No, tell me.
Helle Anker. Cause of death:
cardiac arrest following loss of blood.
Was she alive when he cut her up?
Unconscious.
I've found residues of chloroform
in the airways and lungs. Old school.
The sternum was opened by something
mechanical, not saw-toothed.
I'm guessing by a large angle grinder.
- Knowledge of anatomy?
- Not necessarily.
Open up and pull out. You don't need
to be a surgeon to do that.
Next man. Fabian Christensen.
Suffocated. No other damage to the body.
No missing parts or organs.
- Two murderers.
- Or someone who likes change.
The lipstick they have in common.
That came out in the press,
so it doesn't necessarily mean anything.
Shall we talk about the other thing now?
Okay.
Jennifer Norén. Family?
What have you found out?
I wasn't sure what I should
be looking for.
Anything abnormal.
- The girl was often sick.
- Unnaturally often.
If you mean more often
than average, I would say yes.
I mean that someone made her sick.
Someone with Münchausen-by-proxy.
It is, of course, possible, but there
is nothing to confirm it.
One cannot be so sick on her own.
It's unusual, but it's not impossible.
If you want my professional opinion,
from what I have read -
- there is nothing here
that points to a crime.
- But it could have been.
- Of course.
But that's not how we do things.
Neither you nor I.
We believe in evidence.
- The police were here today.
- Oh, why?
They're looking for a connection
between my video blog and the murders.
You've found it. Where was it?
What are you talking about?
- Have you laid it there?
- No.
Ah. So it must be Karen.
- Do you think I could pull off leather pants?
- Yeah, I think so. Why?
Because ...
The officer who was here had
leather pants on, and it looks so good.
- Was it a Swedish officer?
- Yeah.
- Who's investigating the Helle Anker murder?
- And Fabian Christensen, yeah.
She was over in the Malmo department.
Was it Helle Anker who
was killed in that truck?
It must have been, yeah.
Hans?
- Saga Norén, Malmo Police.
- It's Lillian.
Is Hans nearby?
Do you know where he is?
We should have met at 7:30,
but he didn't come.
I thought that maybe something happened,
or he would have called.
- Have you called him?
- Yeah, but he's not answering.
Did you have a fight? That could explain
why he doesn't answer when you call.
Yes, but we haven't fought.
Would you please see
if his car is still there?
- His car is in the garage.
- Would you please do me that favor?
Okay.
Some of you know me.
My name is Linn Björkman.
I'm taking over while Hans is away.
Until we know why
Hans Pettersson has disappeared -
- we assume that it is not voluntary.
We have added staff,
and all resources are available.
No one may speak with the press.
Report to me every hour,
or when you have new information.
You know what we need to do. Thanks.
- Shall we get a cup of tea?
- Yeah, thanks.
- How's it going?
- We don't know why he disappeared.
He was abducted.
The closest I can come is a
four-year-old email in his trash.
- Aleksander Dover.
- Released yesterday. Eight years for robbery.
He apparently threatened
Hans from prison.
- Do you know where he is?
- He got a temporary apartment.
But according to the landlord,
he never moved in. I can dig further.
Good, do it, and print that there.
- Is that something new?
- Yeah.
- Stronger?
- Mm.
I need to get some sleep.
I know that it's very early.
- Lillian?
He knew that Dover would get out.
Why wasn't anything done?
He didn't say anything. It's up to
the individual to ask for protection.
- And he didn't do that.
- I hadn't heard anything before now.
It's worth checking.
Do we know where Dover is now?
John's working on it.
What are you doing here?
Lillian called me.
I have an address.
What is this place?
Dover has been here in connection
with two cases. The owner is unknown.
It seems like someone is
in there, at least.
Aleksander Dover!
Saga Norén, Malmo Police.
We want to talk to you.
Can you open up now?
Come in.
Hans Pettersson.
- What about him?
- Where were you at 7 PM?
I was here.
I was just released, so I'm just
trying to take it easy.
So you didn't find yourself
in central Malmo?
No.
If I tell you that you were seen
in Malmo, what would you say?
- That they're lying.
- It was right by the police station.
That's why we're here.
You threatened Hans Pettersson in prison.
Do you think it's totally random
that you come out and Hans disappears?
- Has he disappeared?
- Yeah.
He forced me to become
an informer in prison.
Otherwise he would arrest my wife
and take the children from us.
I threatened him, yeah.
He should be as afraid as I was.
As I still am.
I have nothing to do with
his disappearance.
I've sat in prison for eight years.
I don't want to sit there for a lifetime.
Hans would never threaten Aleksander's
family to get him to inform.
- So Dover has nothing to do with it?
- He's lying about Hans.
I think he seemed surprised
when we asked about Hans.
And you believe that?
- Maybe he got into drama in prison.
- I don't believe that.
In any case, we'll put surveillance on him.
- I want to concentrate on this.
- Okay. I'm on it.
No, you'll take over the
Christensen and Anker killings.
There was too little blood by the car
for him to be dead.
If he were going to die, there was no
reason to do it elsewhere.
So it's probably kidnapping.
When it's not custody cases or trafficking -
- there's usually a demand for ransom.
Statistically, very few ...
I know that you want to cheer me up,
but can you not be quiet?
Okay.
Do you need a hug?
No, thanks. It's fine.
Your colleagues were looking for you,
but they left.
I'll demand two million to release you.
Apparently there are often
ransoms paid in secret.
So as to not encourage crime.
It's for my family.
Can you remember them?
Samira and the girls.
Samira. Samira, do you want a little wine?
Gather around. We've received a video.
- What video?
- A demand came for two million.
- How did we get it?
- Attachment from a Hotmail address.
- Are you sure you want to see this?
- Yes.
Good, let's begin.
John, try to go back to the newspaper.
- I've seen that paper at Dover's place.
- What are you saying?
I've seen it. I recognize that
coffee ring. It was at Dover's place.
That swine has my family, my children.
Anyone but him.
Now she doesn't need money.
Johnny has money.
He has my money and my life.
I don't need to send more videos.
I don't need to prove that you're alive.
So you don't need to be alive.
The basement is empty.
The house is searched. It's empty.
There's no one here.
English subtitles by S.E.
kyckling@protonmail.com