PREVIOUSLY
The point is, the work is
called 'The Perfect Family'.
There's also another piece
called 'The Nightmare'.
- Do the pieces have anything in common?
- They belong to Freddie Holst.
I invest in unprofitable companies
and make them profitable.
No one will give me work.
You can buy my photos.
Do you want a job?
Mail me at
L369G42@russmail.com
If there's a number or character
for every victim, we have three left now.
That's Håkan. He was here yesterday.
There was a car in the driveway over there.
- What kind of car was it?
- A yellow car.
Your dad had blue marks on the sides of his
nose. Damage that can occur from strangling.
I don't know what you're talking about.
We own a house. It's ours.
- Are you in?
- Three thousand and this here.
- It's about the threats, I suppose.
- Which threats?
Saga was at my place last night,
and it was extremely unpleasant.
- I have bad news.
- Did something happen with Hans?
No. Your mother was found dead.
EPISODE 7
THE BRIDGE
Do you have a pair of
underwear I can borrow?
- I have my period.
- Okay. You don't want a pair of panties?
- You mean Alice's?
- They're in the bedroom, in the
other dresser drawer.
Then I'll borrow a pair.
I don't need to get them back.
That's okay with you, isn't it?
Alice?
You, breakfast is ready.
It's finished.
Linn called. They've found
more bodies in Sweden.
Who found them?
An anonymous tip was called in. When the
police came, the cellar door was broken.
- A break-in, then?
- It looks like it.
- Do we know who the victims are?
- Likely the owners, but that's unconfirmed.
Hi.
- Saga Norén, Malmo Police.
- I'll be right there.
These are the house's owners,
Filip and Inger Johansson.
- Were any body parts missing?
- Not as far as we know.
But we found these.
- Håkan Ekdahl's.
- Mmhmm. Merry Christmas.
- How long have they been sitting like this?
- At least a day.
The batteries are dead, and
they last at least 24 hours.
- Do they have brand marks in their mouths?
- Let's see.
It's important that they be sent
quickly to Forensics in Lund.
We usually do that.
What the hell ...
What can a disembodied brain symbolize?
Braindead. An idiot. Mastermind.
- The brain behind something.
- What about the apple in the mouth?
Do pigs also have that
for Christmas in Denmark?
Yeah. Maybe he was a pig.
In any case, this points to Holst.
On the list Emil gave us,
there was 'Canceling Christmas'.
- Was someone living down here?
- Maybe.
If they also have symbols in their mouths,
there's only one symbol left in the code.
It could suggest that there's
only one victim left.
I'm thinking Freddie Holst.
Why point to Holst
if he's the next victim?
I don't know.
To scare him, maybe.
I didn't see Alice and
the girls this morning.
- Should you have?
- I usually do.
You decide when you want to see them,
so you probably didn't want to see them.
Yeah, maybe. But I missed them.
Well?
- We need an advance.
- Who is 'we'?
- Jeanette and I.
- What would Jeanette need money for?
- Okay. I need an advance.
- You got 28,000 yesterday.
You've gambled it away.
- We have an old house in Skåne.
- Yeah. Jeanette told me about it.
That's why I need an advance.
You've gambled the house away.
To whom?
- It doesn't matter.
- To whom?
His name is Simon Mortensen.
We have an agreement. You get the
money when I get the child.
It's not ...
... legal to buy a child.
To sell a baby is certainly not legal.
We're not selling the child.
- Jeanette is a surrogate mother.
- A surrogate mother only gets her expenses paid.
But perhaps you'd rather have
that than half a million?
No. Fine.
I thought so.
Colbert will drive you back.
Hopefully for the last time.
Come on.
Before the show, we talked a lot
about involving the relatives.
And there were new casket models,
new color combinations ...
It will be fun. Don't look so sad,
like I'm leaving you for them.
Pick me up tonight?
The train from Göteborg
arrives at half past nine.
Good. Then maybe we can stop
by my place on the way home.
So I can pack a few things.
- What things?
- Underwear, some clothes, toothbrush.
It will be easier, now that I'm
staying with you sometimes.
Chin up.
- Happiness is a choice, no?
- Go now, so you don't miss the train.
See you tonight.
Do you have time to meet today?
Hi, Claes! Of course.
When and where?
You don't know me. You don't know
what's best for me.
I don't need to know you
to know that you should leave Marc.
Me and Marc, we love each other.
Sometimes we love the wrong people.
Yeah, you know all about that.
Do you think I can't hear you?
That we fight?
That doesn't mean anything.
We're good for each other.
It's different than you and Marc.
What's it to you, when
I'll soon be leaving?
- I think about you.
- Yeah, of course you do now.
No, not just now.
I'm going to be a father, thanks to you.
That is the biggest favor I can get.
It's not a favor. It's business.
It doesn't matter.
I want you to have it good
when you've left us.
And Marc.
Jeanette ...
You will always come in second place,
and you are worth more than that.
I haven't thought of leaving Marc.
I'm not coming in second place.
- Your house in Skåne.
- What about it?
He gambled it away yesterday.
Second place, Jeanette.
The sooner you realize it, the better.
Hi.
- It's been a while.
- Do you have time?
What does it look like?
- I could use an appraisal.
- Okay.
This.
- It's a knock-off.
- No, I don't think so.
- He wouldn't have a knock-off.
- You can get 1500.
- It's worth ten times that.
- So sell it elsewhere for ten times that.
No, okay, fine. Then give me 15.
Five, ten ... one, two,
three, four, five. 15.
Just a minute!
Thanks for the deal.
'Canceling Christmas'?
Have you seen it?
It's in the museum. Video art.
Edwina Collin, American painter.
Imagine a traditional Christmas -
- meets a hand grenade in slow motion.
- Do you like Christmas?
- No, not especially.
It's a holiday for children.
Do you have children?
No.
Are they officially declared dead?
- Have you checked up on me?
- Yes.
Don't do that.
You shouldn't take it personally. The
right information is the key to the future.
We have three new killings, two new
pieces. Why does all this point to you?
You think it does. Not me.
- We believe there's one victim left.
- And you think it's me.
In any case, we'd like to offer
you and your wife personal protection.
Thanks, but no thanks. I have cameras,
alarms, and my own security guards.
So if there's nothing more ...
Now you've been offered, anyway.
- You wanted to show me something.
- Yeah, I just need to finish.
No, now. I'm busy.
- What is it?
- Look for yourself.
Woman, medium height.
No visible fractures.
- What has she been buried in?
- Clay.
- Weren't you busy?
- Yes.
Take the pen there.
It doesn't seem to be the
same type of character as before.
These are rounder.
Do you know what it is?
- It looks like an 'A' and a percent sign.
- No, it's not.
You didn't know what it was.
It's probably an 'L' or a 'G'. I just
don't know from which alphabet.
- How many alphabets are there?
- Around 40.
Many of them are no longer in use.
You can take the photos with you.
Yes, I've already done that.
Åsa Holst's pregnancy is a fake.
Worth a little more?
Don't worry! You'll get it.
L and G. From the Glagolitic alphabet.
Which is?
The oldest Slavic alphabet.
Created in 800AD in Macedonia.
So now we know.
Now we're only missing the 6.
So we have one victim left, and
Freddie Holst refuses protection.
The murderer wants to point to Holst,
but we don't know if he's the next victim.
What do we know about
the ones we found this morning?
Filip and Inger Johansson.
They've lived in the house in Ystad
since the early 80s. Pensioners.
He worked in insurance,
and she was a schoolteacher.
- Have we knocked on doors?
- Yes. The neighbors thought well of them.
Nice and quiet.
They kept mostly to themselves.
A yellow car was seen in the
area some days ago.
- We haven't found Söder's car.
- Nor Söder.
The airline confirms that he was on board
the flight to Singapore on the 8th.
- Could he have sold the car?
- Not according to the Transport Agency.
- Did the Johanssons have children?
- No, but they were foster parents.
Since '85.
Do we have a list of the children?
- Not yet, but I've contacted Social Services.
- It's urgent that we get it.
I know, Saga. That's why I contacted them.
There's no connection to any of the
other victims so far.
What about the list of employees
at Anderson TL?
- It's coming soon.
- When?
Soon. In the morning. I promise.
- Good. Can we continue?
- Yes.
- Do you have a moment?
Close the door.
- Sit down.
- It's fine. I can stand.
- How are you doing now?
- Good. You ask a little too often.
It's important to follow up.
If I stop feeling good, I can tell you,
so you won't have to ask me all the time.
I don't know if I should say this,
but there's something you should know.
The preliminary investigation shows your
mother may not have killed herself.
It looks like she was murdered.
Do you have any idea
who could have done it?
I had no contact with her for 20 years -
- but there were a lot of people
who might not have liked her.
Can I go now?
Yeah, do that.
Tell me if you need time off.
I never need time off.
Hey.
- Have you waited long?
- Yeah, but it doesn't matter.
I thought you'd be working
around the clock in Denmark.
- I got upset and left.
- Without notice?
You don't work with Saga, I see.
- They didn't appreciate me, so ...
- What do you do, actually?
I'm watching a Danish family.
Okay.
- Who are you watching?
- Does it matter?
No, I'm just curious.
You're so sweet.
You probably don't know them.
- What do you want?
- Two cappuccinos, please.
They're well-known in Denmark.
- Soy milk in mine.
- I'll fix it up.
- Holst is their name.
- Freddie Holst?
- Who gave you this assignment?
- I don't know.
- How did you get in contact?
- Email.
Look at the address.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Exactly what was the assignment?
I watch the house and send
photos of them as they come and go.
I report what happens.
You were there this morning.
What kind of work is that?
Is that even legal?
I don't have so many clients now.
I need to have a roof over my head.
- Can you stay still?
- Me? Am I bothering you?
- How do you get the money?
- In my account, when I deliver the photos.
- Can you track money from an email address?
- There's a faster way, maybe.
We can send a file with a virus,
so I can track the computer.
- That can take time before it's opened.
- He usually responds right away.
- You're doing it again.
- Am I? Shall we do that?
I need a photo.
Take this.
What, do you owe money or something?
No, I'm just buying something.
Or buying it back.
- How much can I get for it?
- What do you want for the lot?
Ah, we've gotten a fucking email.
Exciting.
- Whose is this?
- I have no idea.
Okay, but this guy is a cop.
Now. I have it. I'm in.
Do you have a price or what?
- 6000.
- 6000?
Okay.
I was going to offer you 7500,
but that's fine.
The signal is coming from Copenhagen.
Vestmannagade.
I'll contact Lillian.
- Keep us updated.
- Of course.
I'm coming!
- John, what's happening? Anything new?
- The signal isn't moving.
The Danish police are on the way.
Fuck.
- We came too late.
- I understood that.
- It turned onto Njalsgade.
- What are we looking for?
A computer, ipad, or cell phone.
We don't know which, but it's moving.
- Coming up on Ørestads Boulevard.
- Got it. We'll be there soon.
It's turning.
It's stopped.
- In a parking lot by the concert house.
- Do you have an exact location?
It's completely stopped there.
There's a yellow car.
John, can you check registration
number UUF 294?
It belongs to Kjell Söder.
It's empty.
- Where is it?
- Wait. Now it's moving again.
The train!
Send reinforcements to all stations!
Where is the blue light?
What? No, it's not there!
It's on the back seat.
For fuck's sake, man!
The train stopped. He's getting off.
He's moving to...
A shopping mall. The mall!
Go in the building. He's inside.
- John! John, where should we go?
- Farther into the building.
If you're on the same floor, you
should be passing him.
Wait.
He's going out again.
- Where should we go?
- To the other side of the metro.
- Where are you now?
- On the other side.
It's right there.
Fuck! We lost the signal.
They lost the signal.
Do you know how dumb it feels
to wait for someone who doesn't come?
My agent wanted to meet with me.
They were going cuckoo with the bookings.
And a text took too long to send?
I thought I could make it,
but that didn't happen.
Sorry.
Can I come in?
Åsa?
- You're sending mixed signals.
- What do you mean?
You invite me to your talk, but you don't
want to meet, and now you come here.
- There's an explanation for that.
- I'd like to have it.
Annika, whom you met
at the opening ...
Yeah, I saw her in Malmo.
She comes to all of my talks.
She's pursuing me.
- Do you have a little stalker?
- It's actually not funny.
I don't know how to get rid
of her. She's crazy and jealous.
Report her to the police.
Her funeral business is
handling Dad's burial.
But you're doing well for yourself.
You can just switch undertakers.
Yeah, I probably can.
Who is that?
Ah, that's our cleaning lady.
- Is Freddie home?
- No, he isn't.
It would mean a lot to me
if you'd come to Dad's burial.
As you know, you were his favorite.
- If you can.
- If I can? Because of Freddie?
What does your stalker say about it?
I'll fix it before then.
- What are you doing here?
- I was visiting Åsa.
Why?
Because she wanted to meet me. She
decides for herself who she meets.
Sure, but not you.
You think you can control
everyone and everything.
But just like all empires fall, and one
day your little empire will fall.
In your dreams.
- Yeah.
- Are you coming?
No, I'm going home.
I'm completely soaked.
You're behaving weirdly today. You
seem irritated and out of balance.
I've had a really shitty day, okay?
Because you didn't see your family?
No, that's not why.
We tried to send a new email,
but it came back.
It was rejected. The email address
is no longer in use, so we can't track it.
In that case, he must have figured
out how we were tracking him or her.
So we don't need you anymore.
You can go.
Okay. See you later, no?
- Good.
- Bye.
- Thanks for the help.
- Is that her job, spying on people?
No, she's a photographer, but she's
had a hard time finding work.
We've talked to Holst. He'll get
police protection outside the grounds.
- He agreed to that?
- We told them about the surveillance.
We need the videos from the
metro station and the mall.
- Lillian is going through the material.
- I want John to look at that.
I trust that the Danes can
analyze surveillance footage.
I don't.
- What about the list of foster children?
- Social Services is mulling it over.
It's classified, but I'm working on it.
- Hi. Are you Saga?
- Yes.
- Kjell Grankvist.
- Saga Norén, Malmo Police.
This is regarding the murder of
your mother, Marie-Louise Norén.
- Why do you want to talk about her?
- I'm from Internal Affairs.
You're only called if an employee
has committed a crime -
- or has made other mistakes.
We can also help if a family member
is a victim of a crime.
So where were you when
your mother was murdered?
I don't know the time of death.
There.
I was in the cemetery.
- Why?
- I'd gotten an email telling me to come.
There was someone who claimed
to have information about the case -
- but no one came.
- And you went alone?
- Yes. It was a demand from the sender.
But you said something.
To your supervisor, for example.
No.
Why not?
She had criticized my performance,
and I wanted ...
... to get back at her.
So there's no one who can
confirm that you were there.
No.
- But I still have the email.
- Excellent. I want to see that.
Your mother said that
you had threatened her.
- She lied.
- Why would she do that?
She didn't like me.
How did you feel when
she showed up again?
I don't know.
Try to put words to your
strongest feeling.
You hadn't seen each other
for how many years?
20.
So she's standing there after 20 years.
You don't like each other ..
How did you know that
I didn't like her?
I'm sorry. I assumed it was mutual.
- Did you like her?
- No.
But I never said that
I didn't like her.
Yes, you have, actually.
While questioning Morten Anker.
Your partner Hanne Thomsen heard it.
So how did you feel?
I ...
I was afraid.
I want to take a
DNA test from you.
It's routine. It's just to
completely exclude you -
- if we find unknown DNA
at the crime scene.
Open your mouth, please.
Thanks. We're finished for today.
I can maybe get that
email on the way out?
Yes.
- Thanks for your help. You'll hear from me.
- Are you okay, Saga?
Committed suicide because of
incredible affair with Anna Ekdahl
Hey.
You're late.
I was reading an article about Anna
Ekdahl and her 17-year-old lover.
Why didn't you tell me that
you're Paparazzi?
I'm not. I'm a photographer.
As a photographer you sneak around
and take photos of people's private lives.
Sometimes, yes. But you know what?
Without me they're nothing.
How can you defend your work
when he killed himself?
It wasn't my fault.
He gave me the tip. He wanted
the photos to be published.
So you hadn't received threats when
you asked me to check that number.
No, I hadn't.
I broke the law to help you.
You know that, right?
It's only wrong if you're caught.
Is that how you see things?
Everything is alright,
so long as you don't get caught?
You're leaving now?
I think we shouldn't see
each other for a while.
It must not come out, that you're here.
Yet you walk around
outside the house.
I don't walk around. I was only
going to the kitchen to get food.
I don't think you understand
how much is at stake here.
We are not just anyone, Freddie and I.
It isn't about money -
- and it isn't about whether
it's legal or illegal.
I have pretended to be pregnant,
and if that were to come out ...
Then why are you doing it? Why didn't
you just get a proper surrogate?
Because it should be my child,
and no one must believe otherwise.
No, do you think I'm senile?
So keep away from the house!
And Freddie. Keep away from him, too.
- Hello?
- I've been trying to get you all frigging day.
- I've been busy all day.
- With gambling away our house again?
Is it Holst who said that?
So you did?
Yes, but listen. I got
7500 today alone.
I have enough to get
the house back. I promise.
You've removed their
clothes and things.
Yeah. They're in the utility room.
I haven't thrown them out.
I was questioned by someone
from Internal Affairs today.
Why?
They think I have something
to do with my mom's death.
She took her own life.
No. It's a murder investigation now.
Are you saying she was murdered?
Yeah. It looks like it.
And they suspect you did it?
Yes. He's lying.
Internal Affairs has nothing to do with
crimes against family members.
That is out there.
Unless she wanted it
to appear that way.
She said that I threatened her.
- Did you?
- No.
But she wanted to set me up for it.
To frame you for murder?
- Why would she do that?
- As revenge.
- As revenge for what?
- You can't ask about that.
Okay. Okay.
Saga, where are you going?
The toilet.
I just thought you would leave.
- Do you want me to go?
- No.
- Åsa says you're here too often.
- I won't be here long.
- What's that?
- Don't you recognize them?
- Sure, but where did you get them?
- I bought it.
It's a gift. Only for you.
Not Marc.
Why did you do this?
Jeanette, I said that I'm
thinking about you.
Thank you.
Remember what I said. Drop that loser.
Goodnight, Freddie.
- Have you been at her place again?
- Her name is Jeanette.
Do you need to be there so often?
She lives here now.
I see her two or three
times a day.
Please.
Åsa. She's pregnant with our son.
It doesn't feel like that.
It doesn't feel like it's mine.
We wanted to have a child, no?
But we can't have children.
I can't have children.
That child is yours and hers.
I have nothing to do with it.
That's why I don't want her
to live here, or to have to see her.
If the child just showed up, then ...
But when I see you two together ...
Åsa. Can't you see it like this?
We're renting her body for nine
months, so the child is yours.
And then we'll never see her again.
Lillian. I want to talk to you.
Yeah. What happened?
As you know, Hans' autonomic
nervous system isn't working.
Now we've found out that
his brain function isn't good either.
He is braindead.
It's the respirator that's
keeping him alive.
Sometimes people wake up again.
After being in a coma, yes.
But braindead ...
I'll ask you to think about the
future and eventual donations -
- and what we will do
regarding the respirator.
- May I see him now?
- Of course.
Oh, hi, John.
Damn, you're here already?
Yeah. I put some reports
on Saga's desk.
It's all the employees and firings
from Andersen TL.
Two have previous convictions. One for
abuse, and one for drunk driving.
- What about the list of foster children?
- That's Linn's job. Ask her.
- Emil Larsson ...
- What?
There's an Emil Larsson who was fired.
Is it that Emil Larsson?
- Who?
- The museum guard.
The one who tipped us off about the
connection between Holst and the pictures.
I don't know. Does he
work at Andersen TL?
There is, in any case, someone
with that name who does.
Did. He was fired.
- Do you have photos of the employees?
- No.
- Sorry. No photos.
- You have no photos of your employees.
- Why was Emil Larsson fired?
- Last in, first out.
Did he know Kjell Söder?
- We all know each other here.
- Could he have borrowed his car?
I don't know.
Did Emil mention that he worked at
another place? A museum?
No.
And you have no photos
of your employees.
- Do you have any parties here?
- Yes, we do. Why?
Come.
We need to identify a
former employee.
An Emil Larsson.
Do any of you have photos
of Emil Larsson on your phones?
- It could be from a party.
- Saga Norén, Malmo Police.
We've gotten the list of foster
children from Social Services.
One name is familiar.
- Okay. Thanks.
- Saga.
Emil Larsson was also on the
list of foster children.
English subtitles by S.E.
kyckling@protonmail.com