Previously
Helle Anker. I've found traces
of chloroform in the airways and lungs.
Did someone take her heart?
Morten Anker. After basic training, went
to Helmand Province in Afghanistan.
Everyone thinks it was me,
but I didn't do anything to her.
I have nothing against homosexuals, but
why should they get married in church?
That question I ask you,
Fabian Christensen.
His heart is still there.
- Have you been in the bedroom?
- Yeah.
- Have you seen my necklace?
- No, sorry.
Stop following me or I will report you.
- You think that it was my fault.
- I know that it was your fault!
Hans Pettersson disappeared, and we're
assuming that it's not voluntary.
EPISODE 3
The subscriber cannot answer your call.
Leave a message after the tone.
Hi, it's me again. Morten.
I don't know if you're hearing this, but
I'll call back tomorrow at 10:00.
It would be nice if you'd pick up.
Who's there?
Hi, it's me again. Morten.
I don't know if you're hearing this -
- I'll call back tomorrow at 10:00.
Why the hell don't you answer?
How did you find me?
What happened? Fuck, man!
- What do I do?
- Listen ...
The Bridge
Welcome.
Last night Police Commissioner
Hans Pettersson was abducted.
We have received a video of Hans
and a demand for ransom money.
We want to hear from people who have
been in the garage by Vidungegatan 5 -
- last night around 7:00
and may have noticed something.
We'll keep you updated -
- but we ask that you show respect for
both us and Hans Pettersson's loved ones.
- How large is the ransom?
- We won't disclose that.
- Do you have any suspects?
- Have the police received threats?
He would give us money,
but it was gone.
Yes, quite a lot of money from
the robbery was never found.
I don't know where it was from,
but it was gone.
He wanted to fix it.
He had a plan.
To kidnap Hans. You think that
it could have been his plan.
- I'm sitting here, aren't I?
- Yes.
Do you know where he could be?
There's a place he usually stays.
Is this the place?
No, that's not it.
It's another place.
He was sitting here.
- But he was released.
- Three shots close to each other.
Chloroform.
- Are there other people after Hans?
- It looks like it.
Saga Norén, Malmo Police.
Henrik, there's something for you
from the technicians.
Thanks. The toy and the toy food can be
bought at any toy store on the internet.
The clothes come from the big chain stores,
and there's a brand on the dolls ...
No DNA found by Helle Anker.
No fingerprints, either.
There are, however, fingerprints
on the door of Fabian Christensen's car.
They come from neither him
nor his wife.
- Are you married?
- What's that?
No. Are you?
Yeah. Rather, we divorced in the spring.
She's moved home to Denmark -
- so it's been slightly difficult
with our daughter, Julia.
It sounds difficult.
The lipstick that was used comes
from a brand called FeliCity
Do you want to know why you're here?
Yes, thank you.
When people find large amounts of blood
in a truck at their work -
- they usually ask questions.
Do you know what they ask about?
No.
"What's happened?
Did someone get hurt?
Do you know whose blood that is?"
You only asked when you
could get your truck out again.
Yeah, I guess I'm not
the curious type.
No, maybe not.
FeliCity ...
- Yeah, what about it?
- We've done a background check on it.
You sit on the board for FeliCity.
That's correct, yeah.
Do you want to know
what this has to do with the case?
As I said, I'm not the curious type.
Fabian Christensen and Heller Anker
had smileys painted on their faces.
It was with lipstick from
the brand FeliCity.
So what are you saying?
That I would have killed Helle Anker
at my work?
And then used makeup from a business
that I'm a board member of?
- Wouldn't that be a little stupid?
- Yeah, maybe.
But occasionally killers feel safe.
They think they're superior to the police.
They're completely confident that
they will never be caught.
But what do I know?
I don't know you.
Maybe you're just stupid.
Danish police went there when
Emergency Services was called -
- but they couldn't identify him. Then we
found your business card in his pocket.
Yes, you said that on the phone.
Do you know who found him?
It was someone homeless. Emergency
Services might have a name. He's in here.
It's Morten Anker.
Did he say anything?
No, he was never conscious.
He died on the way here.
- How many shots was he hit by?
- Three. All three in the chest.
- What are you doing?
- I need to see the damage.
Three shots. Virtually the same pattern.
So you mean that the one who shot
Dover also shot Morten Anker.
It's possible.
And that person has Hans now.
The cases are connected. Helle also
had traces of chloroform in her airways.
It can't be a coincidence.
- I will take over the murder
cases from the Danes.
- Yes, of course.
Make sure that the technicians
prioritize the bullets from these two.
I want one hundred percent confirmation
that this was the same weapon.
We assume that it is linked to Hans.
Continue on that track.
Peter Krogh? Hello. My name is
Henrik Sabroe, Copenhagen Police.
- My partner, Saga Norén.
- Malmo Police.
How did it go with him?
He died. Did you see the perpetrator?
No. I heard someone who ran off.
- Did you know him well?
- Not at all.
I didn't even know his name.
- His name was Morten Anker.
- Okay.
So do you know who his
brother is, or what?
His brother?
It was his brother who shot him.
That was what he said.
"My brother shot me. My brother shot me."
He doesn't have any brothers.
Elias is four years old.
I don't think that he did it, but
Morten has a brother. That's what I mean.
- Elias is his half-brother.
- I know that, Wiki.
Sometimes people call their half-siblings
their siblings, do they not?
So maybe Morten has more half-siblings.
Why didn't you say that straight away?
I had to convince you -
- that I didn't believe a four-year-old
had shot two people in two countries.
- It sounded as if that was what you thought.
- Oh, did it, Saga?
I'm all in.
Full house.
Two pairs ... or better full house.
- Hi. Are you home?
- Yeah.
- He's kicking. Do you want to feel?
- No, that's okay.
I didn't hear that you were coming.
Where have you been?
I've just been all around.
- And doing what?
- Nothing in particular.
And doing what?
How much have you lost?
Dammit, Marc! We need to put
the down payment on that house today!
- Is it today?
- Yeah, it was today.
20,000 before 6:00. Dammit!
I'm sorry.
Did Morten have a brother?
- Only Elias. Why?
- Are you sure about that?
- How can you be?
- I am.
And Villy couldn't have had children
with others before or after Helle?
They were together until he died, so no.
Morten was his only child.
Was Helle a lesbian or bisexual?
If she was a lesbian, it may
have affected their sex life -
- and so Villy might have been unfaithful
and had a child outside of their marriage.
In that case, Helle didn't know.
- Does Aleksander Dover
mean anything to you?
- No, sorry.
What about Hans Pettersson?
He's a Swedish policeman.
It's from John.
It doesn't look like Villy had
more children besides Morten.
Helle didn't know that. Morten
probably didn't know either.
There was that little box of
photos in Morten's trailer.
Can't you remember? Right under
the fridge, where the typewriter was.
Here it is.
Here he is together with his mother.
He has a family,
and then he isolates himself.
He might not have
liked his family.
You don't know if they liked each
other just because they look happy.
Look at this.
- It's from Afghanistan.
- Look at the back.
Killbrothers.
Morten, Kevin Larsen
and Lukas Stenstrup.
They were accused of rape and tortured.
Kevin is dead, Lukas is alive.
- How did Kevin die?
- He committed suicide two years ago.
- What about Lukas Stenstrup?
- It's going better for him.
He runs a program for kids
who need extra support.
This applies to work, studies and
contact with authorities.
Lukas Stenstrup?
Saga Norén, Malmo Police.
This is my partner, Henrik Sabroe.
We want to talk to you about Morten Anker.
- Should I go in with this?
- Yeah.
- What's this about Morten?
- He's dead. Killed.
- When did you last meet Morten?
- It was a long time ago, man.
So ... It was last year, I think. He ...
- He was strange that last time.
- And where were you 8:00 this morning?
This morning I was back home eating
breakfast with my girlfriend -
- and then she drove me here.
- Can I get your girlfriend's number?
- Yeah.
Here you go.
Why do you want to know
where I was at 8:00 this morning?
Before Morten died, he said that it
was his brother who had killed him.
- Morten didn't have any brothers.
- He has killbrothers.
- Are you taking the piss?
- Who else would he mean?
I have no idea.
- Haven't I seen you before?
- I don't think so.
I'm really good with faces.
So am I, and I've never seen you.
She confirmed it.
Let us know if you plan to travel.
I'm not going anywhere.
Bye.
I'm finished, so I'm leaving now.
Okay, thanks for today.
There were clean clothes in the
bedroom, so I folded them.
- I had time for it.
- Okay, but in the future we'll do it ourselves.
- Okay. Good. See you later.
- Bye.
Sorry. This was under the door.
Thanks.
You know, our new director
must like to smile.
Better, but warmer
without losing power.
You've been photographed 1000 times.
- That was 20 years ago, Mom.
- Yes, but people can remember that.
We must take advantage of that now.
Yes, let me see ...
It was much better than I thought.
This could also be used.
The one where she's standing up.
That's enough.
- Then we'll take some with the family.
- Is that really necessary?
We are a family firm that
builds homes for other families.
- Don't you have what you need?
- Aren't you having guests tonight?
So it would be nice if you're home
when they come. Håkan!
- Are you coming?
- Yes, we're coming.
You can maybe stand here
to the side of Anna ...
- When will it be announced?
- That I'm taking over the firm?
Some time next week, I think.
Third generation of house builders.
- I was going to fetch a soda.
- In the cooler. Say congratulations to Anna.
- Why?
- She's the new director for EkdahlsHus.
Congrats. Can the workers in Russia
go form a union now?
We don't have an official policy
against unions.
That's hardly necessary when one
has unofficial threats and harassment.
I'll look into it.
- I'm sorry about that. He's ...
- 17 years old and committed.
But maybe we can help each other by
talking about something else at dinner?
Cheers.
Hey, Marc. Did you get those on credit?
Or maybe you got money?
- I'm going to pay you back.
- Okay.
Then let's go for a ride.
- I can't pay you back now.
- You don't need to tell me that.
Shall I take that?
Hi, Marc. Sit down.
Well ...
You owe me 78 thousand.
- If I just get a week ...
- Shut up.
Try to listen, Marc.
In life you don't get shit.
You have to earn it.
Now we're going to play a little game.
Russian roulette.
For every time
this caliber 38 says click ...
... you get an extra day. Go ahead.
- I only need a week.
- Shut up.
Shut up and shoot!
Now put that pistol to your head
and pull the trigger.
Do you understand?
No ...
Do you think I'm a fucking joker?
Now take that pistol -
- and pull the trigger! Look me
in the eyes! Do I look like I'm kidding?
Come on! Take that pistol and shoot!
Shoot!
Do you think I'm a fucking joker? Shoot!
Come on, Marc!
Exactly. That was one day.
Look at me. Dammit, Marc.
You play poker, man.
Before you had an 83.3% chance.
Now it's 69.4.
Those are damn good odds.
Can you do that?
Can you get the money in one day?
Thought so. Pull the trigger.
Come on. Come on, Marc!
That was two days.
Can you do that?
That's 39,000 a day.
Can you do that? Good advice, eh?
Buy as many fucking days as you can.
There won't be a second time.
Pull the trigger.
Pull the trigger now!
Shoot! Shoot now!
Holy shit.
What, Marc?
Look here, you little idiot.
They're blanks. As if I would use
money to off you, man.
You have two days. Fuck off.
We're not finding anything that
links the murders. Nothing.
We haven't even found Anker's
car yet. What are you doing?
I'm reading the reports on Larsen's death.
Nothing suggests anything but suicide.
- Are you thinking about Hans?
- No, I'm thinking about Kevin Larsen.
Saga?
- How did you get in here?
- I said who I was.
- That shouldn't be enough.
- Most people want to see their mother.
Come.
Give me a cup of coffee.
This policeman who disappeared.
Do you know him?
He's my boss and friend.
You have a friend? How nice.
Thanks.
Did you get a doctor to look at
the journals I gave you?
Yes.
Was there evidence that
I did your sister harm?
No, but it couldn't be ruled out.
So I still have to prove my innocence -
- instead of you proving I was guilty?
You were wrong, Saga. Sit down.
It had terrible consequences.
Jennifer might have been alive today -
- if we hadn't lost custody.
Look at me.
I won't accuse you of anything
or demand an apology -
But you have to admit what you
did so we can move on.
A lot is already too late.
Dad died this morning.
Now it's only you and me, Saga.
We're having a memorial service.
I hope you'll at least come to that.
You haven't always hated him.
Sorry to interrupt.
Helle Anker's car has been found.
Shut up, man.
It's a heart.
- Do you think it's Helle Anker's?
- Maybe.
It's a ticket for the ghost train.
What the hell does he want?
Come.
It's Hans!
Call an ambulance!
He has a pulse!
Henrik Sabroe. We have an injured partner.
We need an ambulance in Dyrehavsbakken.
Hurry up, dammit!
- Where are you going?
- I must go in.
No. We're driving back.
- I have to work.
- It's full of technicians.
- They might miss something.
- They miss nothing.
Saga, they have it under control. There's
nothing you more you can do right now.
Come. I'll drive you back.
No, I'll drive myself.
Saga. Can you come with me?
Marc?
Where have you been?
What have you done?
That's why I played today.
I had to get money.
- I'm sorry. I love you.
- I know that!
And I love you too, but you're
just so fucking stupid sometimes!
I've got two days.
Two days? To get 78,000?
How are we going to do that?
We can't just get an SMS loan, right?
- No. I'll find something else.
- No, you won't.
Not this time.
- How are you now?
- Good.
I'll pay for what I broke.
Think nothing of it.
- Can you participate in the investigation?
- Yes, why wouldn't I?
- You seem a little off balance.
- Now?
No, not now, but before.
That was a reaction to finding Hans
combined with a death today.
- What do you mean? Who died?
- My dad.
- I'm so sorry.
- We weren't close.
Even so. Those kind of feelings can
affect one's police work.
My feelings never affect my work.
Hans expects that I'll find the culprit.
- Because you're friends.
- No, because I'm the best he has.
- What's that?
- It came today.
Madman.
We knew that already.
Fabian Christensen.
- Have you gone to the police with it?
- Not yet.
What are you waiting for?
So they're right. I'm not
responsible, but I'm involved.
You're neither responsible
nor involved. You're a victim.
- It's sick.
- It won't be perceived like that.
The whole discussion on the network
will just start all over.
I don't fucking care
how it's perceived.
- I was at the police station today.
- Why?
Because they think I'm involved.
If they find out that
you've had this -
- then we will really look bad.
Lise.
It's my reputation, so
it's my decision.
Hi.
He's lost a hand and a lot of blood,
and he's in a coma.
I just wanted to know
how he was doing.
Saga, it's not easy
being alone right now.
- So call someone.
- Won't you stay?
You're his friend. You like him.
How long have you been sitting here?
A few hours.
I woke up. I don't know why.
The pills usually work -
- so I thought it might be my
subconscious telling me something.
- So I got up.
- Henrik.
I know you want me to
drop it, but I can't.
One time.
They questioned him only one time.
I thought you were going
to ask your new partner for help.
Yeah.
Henrik, you're late for work.
Yeah. Yeah, that's true.
That's true.
Lukas.
If you kill him, you'll
never get your money.
or we can find another solution.
One that both of you
benefit from.
He doesn't need to benefit from it,
but you let him go free.
A kind of installment plan.
Say something! Say what we need
to do to pay that debt off!
You have big balls, eh?
Bigger than your boyfriend's.
I don't have any choice.
There is something
you can help me with.
The technical investigation on
Hans hasn't produced anything yet.
But it was staged and lighted like
with Christensen and Anker.
The bullets that killed Morten Anker
and Dover came from the same weapon.
The theory is that the targets were Helle
Anker, Fabian Christensen, and Hans.
Dover got in the way when he kidnapped
Hans. Morten was also a threat.
There must be a connection
between Helle, Fabian, and Hans.
There is one.
Yes, I've named Hans Pettersson
in a post -
- because he had spoken highly critically
of me and my opinions.
But you've already been here,
and there's nothing that has changed.
Two connections can be coincidence.
Now there are three. That's a pattern.
What do you know about this, Lars?
I know nothing. Or ...
I know what Lise knows.
And Lise and you both
know more than us, or what?
I've gotten a letter.
"I've gone from words to action
to show my appreciation.
No one understands
what you understand.
I do it without demanding
anything back -
- but it would mean a lot if you
could show me that I'm doing right.
Guide me.
Who should I take next time?"
Typewritten with a picture of
Fabian Christensen from the scene.
It was under her door.
And she has no idea
who it's from?
I think there's a way to find out.
Five Danish soldiers.
Five young men are dead in Afghanistan
under Bente Knudsen's command.
It's not her fault that we send young
men to their deaths in foreign countries.
For me, it's completely incomprehensible
when Afghanistan's troubles became ours.
But if they are to defend
freedom and democracy -
- they should not be under
Knudsen's command.
Early tomorrow she takes off for yet
another assignment with new young men.
Their greatest chance for survival
is if Knudsen is stopped.
I got a letter. A real letter.
That I was very happy
about and grateful for.
In the letter there was also a question.
I think that I've answered that now.
Post it at exactly 5:00 PM.
Is that enough that
he'll go after Bente Knudsen?
The sender wants an objective. Now we've
given him an objective and a time frame.
At 5:00 everyone should be invisible.
I repeat, 5:00, everyone invisible.
All set. She indicated that he
only has tonight to do it.
- Where do you want us?
- Across the road.
Saga.
Not you.
- I won't have you here.
- Why not?
Hopefully the one who hurt Hans
is coming. You shouldn't be here.
- Do you think I'll do something?
- I think there's a risk of that.
- I have good impulse control.
- This isn't negotiable, Saga.
The department at the hospital
is closing indefinitely.
Helle Anker's death made the future
uncertain for the gender-neutral kindergarten -
- but the business is continuing.
Natalie Anker spoke
earlier today.
I'm taking over responsibility
for the kindergarten Helle started.
I'm still in shock over what
happened to my wife -
- but violence or threats of violence
will never silence me.
At the same time ...
Hi. Are you ready?
- Did you win?
- Of course.
Come on, let's grab sushi.
- Honey, I'm far from finished.
- You can't delegate your work?
To whom? Just go.
I'll come in an hour.
- Okay. Then I'll see you later.
- Bye.
Are we even for yesterday now?
Listen ...
I will definitely look into
what you talked about.
For your sake.
- How many have seen it now?
- 1,823 people.
How many have seen it now?
Three more. 1,826.
No activity here.
He still hasn't shown.
Saga, I think I've found something.
I compared Lise's letter with
comments from her blog.
There are 98 comments
from 'Knightrider'.
In 21 of them he uses
the word 'guide'.
That was in the letters to
Helle and Lise. Check 'illuminate'.
- 19 times.
- That was in Helle's and Fabian's letters.
- They're not common words.
- Do you know who Knightrider is?
Let me see ...
John has found something in the
comments section on Lise's blog.
A Rikard Jonsson,
Ringstedgade 21 in Copenhagen.
- That's ten minutes from here.
- I'm on my way now.
- I'll be right there. See you in a bit.
- Good.
Yes, I'm taking over the
kindergarten that Helle started.
I'm still in shock over what
happened to my wife -
- but violence or threats of violence
will never silence me.
Saga Norén, Malmo Police.
I'll be there soon.
Drive to Natalie Anker's instead.
She's the next victim.
No, don't ...
Let me go! No!
Drop the knife!
Stop! Stop!
- Elias!
- He's sleeping.
English subtitles by S.E.
kyckling@protonmail.com