Previously
That was what he said.
"My brother shot me."
Look on the back.
Killbrothers.
- Morten didn't have any brothers.
- He had Killbrothers.
- I will pay it back.
- Take that gun and shoot!
- Are you ready?
- Just go. I'll be there in an hour.
It's Hans!
He has a pulse.
He's lost a hand, and
he's in a coma.
Dad died this morning.
Now it's only you and me, Saga.
Henrik, I thought that you wanted
to ask your new partner for help.
- Saga, I've found something.
- We've found something on Lise's vlog.
A Rikard Johnsson,
Ringstedgade 21 in Copenhagen.
I'm taking over the kindergarten
that Helle started.
Drive to Natalie Anker's.
She's the next victim.
Drop the knife!
Stop!
EPISODE 4
Are you in pain, Dad?
You can't get any more
pain killers now.
I know that you're where
you never wanted to end up.
It's unfair, but you
won't lie here any longer.
Goodbye, Dad.
The Bridge
We're looking for 'Knightrider',
Rikard Johnsson.
A Swede living in Copenhagen.
We're monitoring his apartment -
- but he's hardly ever there.
Yes?
Grew up with his mother in Helsingborg.
Moved at age 17, when she died.
Works as a cleaner.
His employer says
that he's a loner.
The police in Denmark have
said exactly the same thing.
He is wanted.
His passport has been revoked.
- Has he left the country?
- No. He lives in isolation.
He'll go where he feels safe.
- Do we know where he cleaned?
- Not yet.
- His phone?
- The call lists are on the way.
What about Lise? It seems
like Rikard adores her.
He thinks they have a connection.
Maybe he'll go visit her.
- Did he say anything else?
- No, time and place. Here and now.
What the fuck is
he looking for, man?
- On time for once, eh?
- What are we going to do?
You'll go to Sweden
and pick up a bag.
- Which of you is going?
- What do you mean which one?
One gets to stay here as collateral.
That wasn't the deal.
You send your girlfriend
to solve your problems.
They're our problems.
- I'll go.
- No.
No, you shouldn't be alone
with him. You go, I'll stay.
Okay.
Here's the code to the locker
and the address. Drive carefully.
I'll hurry.
- Hi. We've been waiting for you.
- What have I done now?
- Mom, I need to go to the toilet.
- Then run up.
- Do you have good news or bad?
- Most bad, unfortunately.
I thought so.
Here. Help out a little.
So despite my post, he
didn't attack Bente Knudsen.
No.
- How did you find him at the Ankers'?
- We tracked him via the comments section.
- He might want to seek you out.
- Why's that?
He looks like this.
If he contacts you ...
It's Rikard.
- Do you know him?
- He cleans our house. He has keys.
Karen? Karen, open up!
- Karen?
- Mom?
Karen! Karen, open up!
- Rikard! Don't you touch her!
- You need to let us take over.
- Don't you touch her!
- Lise.
Rikard, my name is Henrik Sabroe.
I'm from Copenhagen Police.
I would very much like for you
to let Karen go.
Rikard?
Just try to talk to me, Rikard.
I want Lise, otherwise Karen dies.
We'll make sure, but just let
Karen go so that we can talk about ...
No, I want Lise,
otherwise Karen dies!
Rikard, I won't talk
before you release Karen.
There are reinforcements on the way.
Hopefully they'll be here in fifteen minutes.
This is your fault.
- How's that?
- He knows that I've helped you.
I can get in and
take Karen's place.
You mustn't do that.
You said that you could 'get in' ...
- There's another way.
- You will let Karen go.
No matter what you have done -
- you were never close
to killing a child.
You've already crossed one line.
You don't need to cross another.
Shut up.
Rikard, there's something that goes
to pieces inside if you do that.
It will never be the same again.
Do you understand what I'm saying to you?
If she dies now, then she
takes something of you with her.
Shut up.
To lose a child ... Life is
never quite whole again.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
I don't know if you've tried to undo
something, but a child ...
I'll kill her!
Where's Saga?
-In there.
- Come on, man.
- Karen?
- Calmly.
You ...
Rikard, can you hear us?
- I've done everything for you!
- Talk to him.
I know that! I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Will you please be so kind
as to not harm her?
I'll come in if you let her out.
Let her come out,
then I'll come in.
Shut up.
- Rikard, can you hear us?
- Karen.
Shut up! Everyone shut up!
- Mom!
- Rikard, take it easy now.
Shut up ...
Drop the knife.
Mom!
Saga!
Alright.
Saga, it's fine. Come.
It's totally fine. Come here. Drop it.
Like that. Yeah, just like that.
It's really fine. Come on. Release it.
Here. It's fine. Like that.
It's fine.
Come in.
- It's time.
- Okay. I'm coming.
I know that you're sitting and waiting
for wine and hors d'oeuvres in the foyer -
- but you must wait
a couple minutes more.
What have you learned today?
Now that you've changed his tune,
you need to show the man home.
And the boss and Agneta,
who is such an energy waster.
Is that what you've learned?
Is what what you've learned here today?
No, I hope that my
life story has shown -
- that happiness is actually a choice.
All that you need to do right now
starts here and now. It lives here.
The feeling of how you see yourself.
Thanks for listening.
There. Thanks so much.
- Hi, Claes.
- Hi, Annika.
- That was really good. As always.
- Thanks.
- What can I do for you today?
- Will you sign my photo from Örebro?
You skipped the story
about the batteries today.
I forgot that, actually.
Here you go.
- Can I take another?
- Yeah, of course.
I'll be right with you.
Okay. Thanks.
Hi.
- What's your name?
- Rafaela.
No!
Hey! What are you doing?
Give me that! Hey!
What are you doing?
What's happening? Hey!
Linn.
- Have you found him?
- Yes.
- Is he here?
- He'll be here any minute.
I want to be part
of the interrogation.
That's not an option.
You may be allowed to observe,
but you cannot take an active part.
- Okay.
- Excuse me.
Why did you go in?
If the hostage is in imminent danger,
the police officer must ...
Yeah, I know the rules, but
that wasn't what I meant.
- That was what you asked about.
- Okay.
So I'll ask like this.
How has your father's
death affected you?
As I said, we weren't close.
- And that Hans is still in a coma?
- That doesn't affect my work.
So that's not why you've
been a little reckless?
I'm not reckless. I probably saved Karen
and Natalie Anker. It's just my job.
Your mom called.
- Why?
- She's worried about you.
You have not processed
what's happened.
She has no right to
talk to you about me.
She would you like you
to come to the memorial service.
Rikard has been treated.
He's here now.
- And his defender too?
- He doesn't want one.
Helle Anker. Fabian Christensen.
Hans Pettersson.
Tell us about them.
Come on.
A lawyer would say that it's
always best to talk with us.
We're not going to let you go
just because you don't confess.
I really thought you were
proud of what you've done.
Lise may not have appreciated it,
but you have made a difference.
You've surely done something good,
haven't you? You made a real difference.
Just look at these photos.
Helle Anker. Fabian Christensen.
Hans Pettersson.
Shall we start with Hans?
Had they planned to smuggle
it across the bridge?
Yeah.
- Do we know what's in it?
- No.
- Shall we open it?
- I don't need to know that.
Marc owes money
to Lukas Stenstrup.
I think it's payment for
some of the debt.
I don't want to know. Colbert,
just make sure it's resolved.
I will, Freddie.
What was it you said
to Lise in the apartment?
"You failed me."
That hurts.
Then you get angry.
Was that what happened?
Come on.
Linn. They must get him to talk.
- Is he saying anything?
- Not a word.
He will. We have time.
It's not enough. We must connect
him to the murders, to Hans.
Come with me.
It must be very difficult for you.
We're investigating several murders -
- and a brutal attack on a
police chief, not your husband.
You must take a step back.
You cannot come and go as you wish.
- I have employees here.
- Lent to my department, under my command.
I wanted to be accommodating
because I feel for you -
- but in reality that's wrong.
You're personally involved.
You're not thinking clearly.
You don't know what I'm thinking!
- Do you have it good here?
- In this division?
- In my husband's office.
- It's only temporary.
Yeah. It is.
My grandfather risked everything
and started EkdahlsHus -
- so not only my mother, but
all families were given the opportunity -
- to buy and live in a good, solid,
nice house for a reasonable price.
We're now opening our eleventh branch
in the North, but the first in Denmark.
It's about time, isn't it?
Then let's cut the ribbon.
- Good speech.
- What are you doing here?
Saying hi to my girlfriend.
I've booked a table at
a restaurant tonight at 8:00.
- Can you make it?
- I really don't know.
- Stop it. No one knows you in Denmark.
- You never know.
You met your best friend's son
in Copenhagen and ate dinner together.
- Anna.
- Yeah. I'm coming.
I'll try. I'm not promising anything,
but I will try.
Hi.
- How did it go?
- Not so good.
What now? Jeanette?
- I lost the bag.
- What?
There were some men who drove
up beside me and just took it.
Sit down.
Here's 7500. It's not much, but
it's all I could get.
You can also have the car.
Do you have any idea
what that bag was worth?
- Surely more than 78,000.
- Far more than 78,000.
I promise I'll get the money.
I'll get your money.
I'll find a solution to this shit.
Shut the fuck up, man.
From now on you don't owe
me shit. Do you understand?
We're even.
Piss off.
Fuck off.
- Are we really even?
- That's what he said.
How the hell ...
Where did you get the money from?
I sold some jewelry
that I had hidden.
- From me?
- Yeah.
I'm really sorry, Jeanette.
Can we just go home?
- Did it go well?
- Perfectly.
- What's happening?
- He's not saying a word.
Does he think he can go free
by not talking with us?
The motive is attention.
He should want to take credit for it.
He seemed surprised when he saw Hans.
Like he didn't know ...
We've gotten his schedule.
We don't know when they were killed,
but it's definitely possible he did it.
- We'll try another round with him.
- It can wait. You have something else to do.
That's Hans' hand.
He has a ring like that, at least.
Shut up, man.
It's the same again.
Spectacularly staged. Lighting.
Helle Anker dies first. Her heart
and her car lead us to Hans -
- who is missing a hand,
which we find here.
There's nothing that connects
Fabian Christensen with the other three.
No, there's really not.
Could Richard have done this after
he ran away from Natalie's last night?
The doctors say that he has
been dead for 12 hours at most.
- Do we know who he is?
- Not yet.
It doesn't look like
he's missing anything.
Shut up, man.
Hi, Claes.
- Hi.
- Sorry for bothering you.
I read about your dad.
I'm sorry.
- Thanks.
- Was it sudden?
No ...
He had been sick a long time, so ...
Even if one is prepared,
it's always a bit of a shock.
I just wanted to give my condolences
and see how you were doing.
Okay. Thanks.
Do you have someone here,
or do you want to be alone?
I can stay a while.
Come in.
Gather around.
Sorry.
Lars Ove Abrahamsson, 72 years old.
Retired gym teacher from Oxie,
but I want to know more.
He has a sister, Margaretha.
She's on her way home from Gdansk.
Now the question is whether we've got
the right man. Rikard isn't talking to us.
We must decide whether we want
to spend more time with him.
It would seem he read
about Helle's murder -
- and killed Christensen
for Lise's sake.
- Do we have facts to confirm that?
- Only Fabian wasn't missing body parts.
Further, we've only found
Rikard's fingerprints on Fabian's car.
And there was a photo of
Christensen in the letter to Lise.
Has Lise Friis Andersen said
anything about Lars Ove on her blog?
Vlog.
Sorry?
If one puts out a video clip instead
of text, it's called a vlog, not a blog.
- No, not as far as we know.
- I can have a chat with her.
In addition, we found a typewriter
at Rikard's place, but no pistol.
Okay. We have him for the
attempted murder of Natalie Anker -
- and so we'll try to
get him for Christensen.
But we assume that Rikard has
nothing to do with these three.
- What is the connection between them?
- We haven't found anything yet.
So we know where to start tomorrow.
Thanks for today. Good job.
Linn. This analysis
at the whiteboard ...
It's usually me who does it.
Since it's my case.
No, Saga. It's our case.
Sit down.
I try to learn about my coworkers,
so I've read a little about you.
Your performance reviews
with Hans puzzle me.
Ah.
It seems like he asked how you
were, and then you were finished.
It may seem unnecessary -
- but it's about developing and
utilizing the staff's skills.
Hans knows me and what I can do.
So he hasn't said that there have
been complaints about you several times?
- Who has complained?
- No coworkers.
Most are witnesses
or other non-suspects.
They have seen you as
insensitive and unpleasant.
- You didn't know anything about it?
- No.
We're in the middle of
a complicated murder case.
I don't doubt that you are
an extremely valuable resource.
But afterwards I will look at
possible sensitivity training.
Coaching or the like.
Ah.
What do you say to that?
I am already well aware
of my limitations.
Limitations are another
word for new possibilities.
Not for me.
- Was there anything else?
- No. You can go home now.
- I knew you would come.
- I knew too.
- Have you ordered?
- No, I waited for you.
Thanks.
You are so beautiful.
It's true.
Does Håkan never give
you compliments?
No, not so often.
He doesn't understand
how lucky he is to have you.
Hi.
- Do you have just five minutes?
- Yeah.
- Hi Karen.
- Hi.
- How is she?
- Good under the circumstances.
- We're just about to eat.
- Yeah, of course.
I just need to know if you know
a Lars Ove Abrahamsson.
No.
Are you sure? Swedish, 72 years old,
retired gym teacher.
Lives in a small community
outside of Malmo, Oxie.
- Why do you ask?
- Because he's dead.
Killed.
You've just arrested Rikard.
So you haven't named
him in your video blog?
No. Does this mean that
it's the same murderer?
There's something to suggest it.
So this doesn't have anything
to do with my videoblog.
That doesn't mean that what you're
doing is okay. Have a good night.
It's getting late.
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
- You look good.
- Thanks.
Lillian. Hi.
I was in the shower.
What do you want?
I want to know if
you'll help me with something.
Of course. What?
Linn would like me to keep a certain
distance from the investigation.
Keep me away, quite frankly.
I need you to give me
access to the investigation material.
I would really appreciate it.
- Of course I will.
- Thanks.
I need to go. We'll talk.
Thanks. Hi.
- Hi. What are you doing here?
- I'm a member.
It seemed like an efficient way
to find someone to have sex with.
Okay. Good luck.
Thanks. Same to you.
- Saga Norén, Malmo Police.
- Frederik Hansen. Hi.
- Shall we have sex?
- Sorry?
Shall we have sex?
That's a bit sudden ...
I'm glad that you persuaded me.
It was just what I needed.
That's what I said.
- Not here.
- Okay. Where's your hotel?
Our model home is
completely furnished.
Think if we could always
have it be this way.
- We can't.
- Why not?
I love you.
But now that's how it is.
- I hate it.
- No.
No, you don't.
Ah, you're sitting here.
You made it sound easy to
find someone to have sex with here.
It is a singles club.
Many of those who come are
looking for something more long-term.
Are you also doing that?
Looking for something long-term?
Why are you asking?
Otherwise your evening must
also have been a failure.
Are you suggesting what
I think you're suggesting?
No, I'm not suggesting anything.
It could be interpreted
that you think we should have sex.
Yes.
Yes, it could be interpreted like that,
or yes, you think we should have sex?
Yes, I think we two should have sex.
Okay.
But it has to be at your place.
- Why? You surely must live closer.
- We'll have a shorter drive to work from your place.
- You're thinking of staying the whole night?
- Yeah. Is that a problem?
No.
Come.
You can get ready and lie down.
Shouldn't we just have
a drink first?
Do you need alcohol to have sex?
No.
Good. Get ready.
Okay.
- What do you like best?
- What?
- I don't know.
I prefer missionary with
my legs in a certain way.
I don't like being touched, but
I can touch you how you want.
I don't want to kiss,
but oral sex is good.
Do you have any wishes?
No. That sounds damn good.
- Do you want to borrow my toothbrush?
- Your toothbrush or a toothbrush?
- My toothbrush.
- No thanks.
- You look tired.
- Do I?
- Yes.
- I just slept badly.
Or else the orgasm usually
drains the muscles of energy -
- and makes a man
feel exhausted.
Thanks for that really great
information, Wiki -
- but I have a little bit
of a sleeping problem.
- Are you ready to roll?
- Yes.
- Do we tell people at work?
- Do we tell people what at work?
That we've had sex.
Does one tell people that at work?
- One doesn't tell.
- Okay.
Marc?
Dammit.
- Good morning.
I let you sleep.
Do you want breakfast?
- No, but coffee would be good.
- You must eat.
I made scrambled eggs. Sit down.
Coffee ...
Have you already decided who
will be in charge of the funeral?
Why haven't you called?
I don't understand what you mean.
I have a funeral business.
Ah, I didn't know that.
I told you after the
reading in Södertälje.
Oh yeah. I had forgotten that.
- I haven't really gotten that far.
- No, that's clear.
But when you're ready,
I can take care of it all for you.
Thanks.
Karin Pettersson is coming today. Hans'
ex-wife. They were together 20 years.
Good.
This should tell us something. The
placement of the bodies. The lighting.
Maybe that's the meaning.
It's not who, but how.
Maybe it's a coincidence
that it's these three.
The person shot Aleksander Dover
to get a hold of Hans.
But no one can come up with
a connection between the three.
Saga.
- I want to ask you a favor.
- What?
I want to ask you to
look at a case.
- What is it?
- An investigation. A cold case.
It's actually closed. Archived.
- Totally Danish?
- Yeah.
2009. Missing persons.
- Why should I look at it?
- Because you might find something new.
- Was it your case?
- No.
I've checked all the cars that passed
the surveillance camera that day.
- A white van. Guess whose it is.
- I don't guess.
The youth center where Lukas works.
I recognize the license plate.
Come.
- Will you look at it?
- When I get time.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
- Yeah, it's our car.
- Who drove it?
It could be anyone here.
The keys hang in a key cabinet.
- Is it not locked?
- No.
But everyone writes in the
driver's log, which is in the car.
Here.
Sorry. It's empty.
The 5th here at 4:50
it was at 181,320 kilometers.
And the next one is the
day after at 10:30 -
- and it was at 181,565.
So someone had also driven
245 kilometers that night.
- And you don't know who.
- I have no idea.
- Was that all?
- Yeah. You can go.
We'll stay and wait for the technicians.
So they can take the car.
- Hello?
- Hi.
Welcome home.
- How did it go in Copenhagen?
- Good, thanks.
- Did you meet up with Ulrik and Gunilla?
- No, I was too busy.
- Hi, Mom.
- What the hell are you doing to me?
- I've just come home from Copenhagen.
- Are you near a computer?
Look at Aftonposten,
then call me.
EUROVISION STAR HAS
SECRET TRYST IN COPENHAGEN.
What did you say her name was?
Her name is Helle Anker.
His name is Lars Ove Abrahamsson.
No. Sorry.
Listen ...
You've worked together
with Hans a long time now.
Yes.
Have you met his new wife?
Lillian?
- Yes, many times.
- Karin.
We want to know if there's a connection
between your ex-husband and these two.
Why did the same person
want to hurt them?
I understand, but I can't
be of help, unfortunately.
What is she like? Lillian?
What is she like?
She's nice. Police Chief
in Copenhagen. Younger than you.
It all went so fast.
Wedding and new flat
and all of that.
I can understand that. If you
think of anything else -
- please call us.
Was he different with her?
He came late now and then. He didn't
do that when you were married.
I understand.
Yeah, many thanks for coming.
Saga. Will you come with me?
- What are we doing?
- Just come now.
- What are we doing here?
- The memorial service is here.
- I know that, but I don't want to be here.
- I support you.
I think that it's
important to say goodbye.
I can't!
Research shows that physical contact
can hasten awakening.
And familiar sounds such as voices.
So I can tell you
what's happening at work.
Linn, your replacement, wanted me
to go to my dad's memorial service -
- but I couldn't.
My mom ...
My mom made my sister
sick in front of me.
Everything pointed to Münchhausen By
Proxy. I had to get her away from there.
Otherwise I was afraid that
she would die.
I couldn't have done differently.
Hans ... It would be really good
if you woke up now.
Hans.
Who was that with
Lukas Stenstrup?
His name is Mehmet. It was he
who drove the car the night of the 6th.
Did he say why?
Yeah. He had to visit
his girlfriend in Lund -
- but one cannot use the
car for private purposes.
Maja Nyrén, the girlfriend, confirms
that Mehmet was there until 4:00.
It fits with the times on the camera.
But we cannot rely on one person.
See if Øresundsbroen has photos,
and if one can see the driver.
Okay.
Good work.
- I'm not in trouble, right?
- Fuck no.
- Who really had the car?
- Just get in.
Reported Missing
English subtitles by S.E.
kyckling@protonmail.com