(panting)
Hurry UP!
Next time, maybe take a leak
before we leave work, OK, dipwads?
Can you read sign language, guy?
Is that your IQ or the number
of dipwads your mother had?
(shivering)
Not you too, Sandy.
Sorry, man. You gotta
hold it till you get home.
I'll see you tomorrow, Sandy.
(shivers)
(gasps)
(horn)
(knocking)
Hey, Sandy, chop chop!
Hey, Sandman?
Hey! Hot dog, come on. Carpe diem.
(clatter)
(screaming)
(creature growling)
By restoring moisture to the documents,
and by a reassembling of fragments,
I can recover a large percentage
of the case material
that was destroyed in my office fire
several months ago.
While this process is tedious,
what I've already recovered
will allow Agent Scully and I to begin work
on the X-Files immediately.
Agent Mulder...
Agent Mulder, I'm reading here
a very pie-in-the-sky report
about global domination plans
by vicious long-clawed spacelings.
Is there going to be data to back
this vague omnibus account?
Yes.
I see your renowned arrogance
has been left quite intact.
You're asking us to accept this report
of a spaceship buried under polar ice
and your death-defying escape from it?
The ice became superheated by the ship
as it rose beneath us, causing it to collapse.
This story is unintelligible
and encourages unintelligible analysis.
I hoped you'd look closely at the reports
of mine and Scully's medical conditions.
These spacelings, Agent Mulder...
They weren't something I saw
in Men in Black?
- I didn't see Men in Black.
- Well, it's a damn good movie.
This may sound like science fiction,
but we can and will prove
the validity of our report.
So the plot... I'm just trying
to get this straight.
The plot is for these spacelings
to take over the planet,
aided by a group of men on Earth...
A conspiracy within our own government.
...who are growing corn in the desert,
which features pollen,
which was genetically altered
to hold a virus,
which will be taken away by bees
whose sting transmits the virus,
causing the growth of an extraterrestrial
biological entity inside the human host?
Which we will prove now that
the X-Files have been reopened.
Your presumption, Agent Mulder,
is far greater than the case you make.
I don't understand.
You justify your reassignment on the X-Files
with little more than a rattletrap account
of high adventure in the Antarctic.
Not to mention some
questionable travel expenses.
Let us remind you that the FBI
is not a school for science
or for the grinding of personal axes.
Hopefully, you can present us
with some material evidence
to support an investigation.
Agent Scully was assigned
to the X-Files as a scientist,
was stung by a bee,
and was infected with this virus.
She is here today with hard
and incontrovertible evidence.
Scientific proof that the virus she was
infected with is in fact... extraterrestrial.
Next time I'll wear a clown suit
and do tricks.
I hoped it wouldn't come up.
I was there because you assured me there
was a scientific basis for what we saw.
Let me remind you once again
that what I saw was very little.
That excuse is not gonna work.
You were there and you were
infected with that virus.
Yes, there is a scientific basis for what
happened to me. I was exposed to a virus.
But as it turns out, Mulder,
that virus is not what you thought.
Look, I can't identify it, Mulder.
I have run three separate tests.
But I can tell you that that virus's DNA
and proteins are very much of this world.
I saw what that virus did.
I saw it generate a new being.
An alien being inside a human body.
It attacks and destroys human cells,
but that is all it does, Mulder.
It creates nothing.
Look, I don't like telling you this.
And I know that you don't wanna hear it.
You can question me and what I saw,
but what you can't question is the science.
There was sloppiness in Phoenix
where they found the body.
The local PD got involved. These were
taken at the scene by a crime reporter.
These were run in the press?
I trumped up a story about
a crazy Indian on the loose.
Never underestimate the public's
willingness to blame the red man for...
what they can't explain.
- How did this happen?
- He was one of ours.
He must've accidentally injected
himself while he was working.
It took just 1 2 hours
for the creature to gestate.
- This thing's alive?
- Yes.
- It's killed a man.
- It's out there somewhere?
As far as I know.
Lord Almighty! We can't have
this thing running loose.
I'm managing the situation.
- Someone's gotta find this thing.
- Someone has to kill it.
The response must be equal to the threat.
Can you dispose of this problem?
Yes.
(door opens)
Wasting your time.
You need evidence. I've just got
to bring it back from the ashes.
Nothing you might restore is gonna help
you, Agent Mulder. It's over and done.
Your reassignment has been denied.
How can it be denied? We're the only reason
the X-Files were reopened in the first place.
- I'm not arguing with you.
- Well, who is?
When will you accept
that no amount of reason
will bring to heel a conspiracy whose
members walk these halls with impunity?
Was there a vote?
Unanimous against.
Excuse me.
I'm no help to you outside
the majority, Mulder.
I don't see that there's a damn thing
you can do for me.
You can break their backs
with proof about this virus.
- Proof that what you say it does is true.
- I don't have that proof yet.
Maybe I can give it to you.
There's a file folder.
It's on the desk in your old office.
Is that something for me?
Agent Mulder?
- Yeah, if you're doing my filing.
- Your filing?
Why are you in my office, Agent Spender?
I think there's been a miscommunication.
I think someone failed to inform you.
If you're saying you were sent to work on
the X-Files, the failure is simple judgment.
I don't care what patronage got you
this job. I put my life in here.
I'm not gonna let some brown-nose
take it all away from me.
I don't believe in
the paranormal mumbo jumbo,
- so don't presume I'm taking your place.
- No? Who is?
(footsteps)
- Fox.
- Diana. Back on your feet.
I guess that's the only way
you can stab me in the back.
I need the patient bandaged and dressed.
We'll be taking a trip.
You want him what?
I'm sure I don't need to repeat myself.
Please get the boy ready.
- But doing that now could kill him.
- Let me put it to you simply.
It's him or it's us.
I wanna remind you that
by not informing local PD
we are in technical violation of state laws
prohibiting contamination of a crime scene.
Why do I bother?
Scully, come here and take a look at this.
Ever seen anything like this?
- What are they?
- According to the investigator's notes,
they're from an attack by
a Native American man on a scientist.
- With what kind of weapon?
- It says in the file he used his bare hands.
His bare hands?
- This is hardwood.
- Uh-huh.
This kind of gouging didn't happen
with anybody's bare hands.
Not without the use of
some kind of an implement.
What is that?
Ah... Somebody broke a nail.
- Is it animal?
- It ain't RuPaul.
The body of the other victim was found on
the sofa, his viscera torn from his torso.
The ME's report says
the times of death were hours apart,
which means that this victim was dead
hours before the second attack.
- So the attacker never left.
- It wasn't an attack.
I think it was celebrating its birthday.
The first victim was infected with the virus.
Right here is where the creature was born.
- Mulder...
- It accounts for the violence to his torso.
The virus producing an extraterrestrial entity
that ripped away his chest
as it birthed itself right here. Look.
Given that scenario, the rate of gestation
would have been less than a day.
It would've been about 12 hours.
OK, forgive the scientific argument.
But you're saying that this was
done by something newborn?
That's exactly what I'm saying.
It was here.
But it's gone now.
- I should take a look.
- It's not here.
Why don't you believe me
when you're so afraid of me?
I'm not afraid.
You think I can destroy you
for what I know, cos of what I am.
You're thinking you could've
destroyed me, too.
And if I don't find this creature, you will.
He'll find it.
(Mulder) I don't see
there's any argument here.
You admit yourself the crime report is a lie.
Mulder, that doesn't mean
that I can just accept your theory.
What does it take?
For this thing to bite you on the ass?
I saw these creatures.
I saw them burst to life.
You would have seen them too,
but you were passed out over my shoulder.
Mulder, I know what you did.
I know what happened to me.
But without ignoring the science, I can't...
Listen, Mulder. You told me
that my science kept you honest,
that it made you question your assumptions,
that by it I'd made you a whole person.
If I change now, it...
it wouldn't be right... or honest.
I'm talking about extraterrestrial life
alive on this planet in our lifetime.
Forces that dwarf and precede
all human history.
I'm sorry, Scully, but this time
your science is wrong.
("Put on a Happy Face" by Tony Bennett)
Wake up, Homer.
I was awake.
- I was just thinking.
- Yeah, that'd be a first.
You're late on your systems check.
If there was a problem,
we woulda heard about it.
Like Arizona's gonna go without
air conditioning for ten minutes.
Hey, Homer. Got something here
in the bleed cooling system.
See that?
- Five degrees off. I'll be...
- Might be in the core reactor.
Nah, nah, nah.
It's gotta be a monitoring glitch.
Phone could start ringing any minute.
You might wanna check it out.
All right.
Brush off the clouds and cheer up
Put on a happy face
(humming)
Start spreading sunshine
all over the place...
(squelching)
- (creature screeches)
- (Homer screams)
(Spender) I want this place sealed off.
Authorised officers only.
This is a closed area.
- What happened?
- You'll have to leave.
We had a call that a man was killed.
A call from whom?
Assistant Director Skinner?
- Let us through.
- You are unauthorised to be here.
You've come here
without cause or permission.
I'm gonna get you censured and demand
a review of AD Skinner's actions.
Diana, let us in here.
I can't. This facility has been
sealed off by the NRC.
A man was murdered.
He was killed in an accident in a reactor
where there was a systems failure.
Why are you here?
Because of a possible connection
to two previous deaths
from a case file that
was stolen from our office.
(Sirens)
- There is a connection.
- Let's get outta here, Mulder.
I hope you know what you're doing, Diana.
I hope you know whose errands
you're running.
I think I do.
We weren't getting anywhere.
It was making it worse.
It's here, Scully, and they know it.
How do they know?
Mulder, how do you know?
Give me the keys and get in the car.
Oh, my God.
Gibson.
Sorry, sweetie.
Gibson? Gibson?
Gibson, sweetheart? Oh, God.
Frankenstein? Really?
No.
No, you've been worked on
by some good doctors.
They did a fine job of your stitches.
You think they were butchers.
They were butchers.
They should've changed
your bandages, Gibson.
You've got some swelling
and some infection.
And you've got a fever.
- Why did they do this to you?
- Cos I can read people's minds.
- How did you get in our car?
- When they weren't looking, I snuck away.
It's easy when you know
what they're thinking.
Why are you here?
They were using me,
cos I can communicate with it.
Communicate with what?
You already know.
You just don't wanna believe it.
The kid could find this thing.
- Mulder, he belongs in a hospital.
- We could get his fever down.
Mulder, you can't just
take him on some snipe hunt.
He belongs in a bed
under constant medical care.
Listen to me. What I'm saying
is in your best interest, OK?
We have to take every precaution
to ensure that nothing happens to this boy,
because, whatever he is, whatever gives him
the ability to do what he does,
he's your scientific evidence.
It's just like we said.
- He could be the key to all the X-Files.
- We don't have the X-Files.
No. But what if he could corroborate
everything that you're saying?
This boy could be our last best chance.
(Diana) Agent Mulder?
Fox, I'm going to get out of the car.
I'm alone, all right?
- What are you doing here?
- I couldn't say anything to you earlier.
I was given this assignment, Fox, OK?
They offered it to me. I took the chance.
I'm listening.
To make sure someone served your interests,
someone who believes in the work.
Hey, you and I found the X-Files together.
Don't forget that.
- Who sent you?
- I'm here on my own.
- Why? To convince me of your intentions?
- Listen to me.
That thing is inside the No.4 reactor building.
We can let them find it and destroy it,
or go find it ourselves.
You need proof, Fox.
You're so close. Why can't you see that?
Mulder, what's going on?
- You take Gibson.
- Where are you going?
To find this thing.
Agent Spender and I got a call. We were on
a plane within an hour in constant contact.
- With who?
- The nuclear regulatory people.
NRC was first on the scene.
They found the victim.
When we got there, it had been removed.
We never saw the body.
- Who removed it?
- I don't know. Couldn't get a straight answer.
Then the NRC sealed off the No.4 reactor
due to a problem with the heat transfer
systems. I believe that was legitimate.
Maybe that's why it's there.
It wants heat. It needs heat.
This thing gestated abnormally fast.
What if heat activates it?
It could spur on the virus
and the development of the entity.
- But it's still seeking heat. Why?
- What if it's still developing?
You don't think what we're looking for
makes sense in any conventional way?
No.
You're gonna be fine, Gibson.
You're gonna be OK.
Let's get a bed ready.
- You're gonna run more tests.
- We're gonna get you well.
You say that, but you're gonna run
more tests, like the other doctors.
We have to run this one test, Gibson.
You wanna make me well,
but you're thinking about yourself
and what you can learn from me.
You're a very special boy, Gibson.
You know that yourself.
I'm a very special lab rat.
(Diana) According to what we could gather,
the victim's body was found near here.
- It's hot in here.
- We're right above the core reactor.
This is part of
the heat transfer cooling system.
- Looks organic.
- Maybe somebody's got the flu.
- (gasps)
- What? What is it?
There's something in there.
(cellphone rings)
(Mulder) Yeah?
Mulder, I found something
you're not gonna believe.
Ditto.
We did blood tests on Gibson. Mulder,
there's evidence of the virus in his system.
- The same virus you were exposed to?
- I'm almost positive.
What does that mean?
I don't know, but I think
we're onto something.
- We're onto something huge, a link.
- I'll call that bet and raise you.
- What?
- Never mind. Just take care of Gibson.
There was a little boy in that room
and he's gone.
Does anybody know what happened
to that little boy?
His name is Gibson Praise!
He was just in that room!
Does anybody know
what the hell is going on?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Let's just calm down.
- That little boy I brought in is missing.
- He can't be. He should be in his bed.
He's not here!
- He's here.
- Where?
Somewhere.
- (pounding on door)
- Open the door, you son of a bitch!
Open the door, damn it! Open it!
Open the door, you...
Fox! I'm gonna go see if
there's some other way in!
Open it! Open this door!
- I told you it was here.
- (creature screeches)
(man screams)
(screeching)
Gibson! Gibson!
- Gibson!
- (alarm)
(shouting)
Gibson! Gibson!
As I said, and as I am
forced to reiterate, Agent Mulder,
the FBI is not here for vendettas
or for the grinding of personal axes.
This holds not just for you,
but for everyone at the Bureau.
You force us to put a point on this,
to make some hard changes.
You and Agent Scully will cease all
material association with the X-Files.
Refusal to do so
will end in immediate dismissal.
A probationary period will be set.
You will now report
to Assistant Director Kersh.
You're not supposed to come here.
It's what was agreed to.
It's the deal you made.
I had to congratulate you,
commend how you handled things.
How you handled Mulder.
I did what I was asked.
You did well, son.
He's on very thin ice now, you know.
Mulder will be back.
As long as he lives, he won't give up.
Well, there are solutions, of course.
Simple but extreme solutions.
I've used these methods.
They have their place.
But not here.
You've killed men.
You can kill a man.
But you can't kill what he stands for.
Not unless you first break his spirit.
That's a beautiful thing to see.
(door opens)
If you shut the door, it'd be harder to see
that I'm disregarding everything I was told.
Everything we were told, Mulder.
They can't take away
the X-Files, Scully. They tried.
You know, Agent Fowley's report to OPR
painted the facts in an interesting way.
I hope you weren't betrayed.
Agent Fowley's report
was a means to an end:
trying to protect the work,
protect the X-Files.
Agent Fowley's report states
that the man you saw attacked
was bludgeoned by an unknown subject.
She makes no mention of a little boy
who is nowhere to be found.
It would seem that her report
protects everything but you.
Agent Fowley took me to that plant
at great risk to herself,
where I saw something that you refuse
to believe in. Saw it again.
And though it may not say it in her report,
Diana saw it, too.
She's certainly not gonna go around saying
that just because science
can't prove it, it isn't true.
I don't doubt what you saw, Mulder.
I don't doubt you.
I'm willing to believe, but not in a lie
and not in the opposite of what I can prove.
It comes down to a matter of trust.
I guess it always has.
- You're asking me to make a choice?
- I'm asking you to trust my judgment.
To trust me.
I can't accept that if it refutes
what I know to be true.
Mulder, these are test results.
DNA from the claw nail we found,
matching exactly the DNA from the virus
you believe is extraterrestrial.
That's the connection.
Which matches exactly DNA
that was found in Gibson Praise.
I don't understand. You're saying
that Gibson is infected with the virus?
No. It's a part of his DNA.
In fact, it's a part of all of our DNA.
It's called a genetic remnant.
It's inactive junk DNA,
except in Gibson it's turned on.
So if that were true, that would mean
that Gibson is in some part extraterrestrial.
It would mean that all of us are.
Visiontext Subtitles: Yasmin Rammohan
(Child) I made this!