(announcer) We interrupt this
programme for breaking news.
(anchorman) 90 miles is how far
officers of the Nevada Highway Patrol
have pursued the blue car on your screen
in a wild chase
right through the heart of Elko,
at speeds approaching
100 miles an hour.
Live on the scene is Chuck Pickering
in the "Fox 11 News" chopper.
Chuck, what can you tell us?
Benjamin, we're heading west following
Route 766, where it feeds off the I-80.
Just under an hour ago, troopers
attempted to pull over the blue car,
which we understand is stolen.
That occurred on the 80 east of Wells.
Since then, this driver has stopped
for nothing and nobody.
- (Benjamin) Any word yet on the driver?
- Not at this time.
What we do think, and what we've
passed on to the highway patrol,
is that, from our vantage point,
we see another person in that car.
See? Right there - a hand.
It just moved. See, in the back seat?
Now, we could possibly have
a hostage situation here,
and obviously the sooner
they bring this vehicle to a stop...
(Sirens)
(Piercing tone)
Unit Six ready at milepost 13.
(man over radio) Coming your way, Six.
(Chuck) That did the trick. The automobile
seems to be coming to a stop.
(Benjamin) What did they use?
(Chuck) It looked to be
a tyre-puncturing chain.
Now the officers are approaching the car.
One of them has opened the door,
and he has hold of the suspect.
He's pulling him out.
He doesn't seem to have a weapon.
(Benjamin) It looks like he doesn't
want to get out of that car.
Vicky! Vicky!
- (officer) Ma'am?
- Please get it out of my head.
Let me go! Vicky!
Vicky! No! No!
(Benjamin) The hostage is OK.
The highway patrol has her.
- It looks like that driver is still fighting.
- (Chuck) He is putting up a fight.
He seems to be a man with a few choice
words on the subject, as you can see.
They're trying to restrain him.
We'll get a wider angle.
See, there's the woman.
What the heck? She's...
Vicky! Vicky!
(Chuck) There, see? She's banging
her head against the window.
What the hell just happened?
- Yeah?
- Uh... Virgil Nokes?
I'm Agent Scully. This is Agent Mulder.
We're with the FBI.
- Jehovah's Witness?
- No, sir. Federal Bureau of Investigation.
But we do have a free copy of
The Watchtower for you, if you like.
This is just a routine check.
We understand that you recently ordered
5,000 pounds of ammonium nitrate fertiliser.
Oh, you people. Come on in.
- Sugar beets.
- Excuse me?
I grow sugar beets.
I got better things
to do with my fertiliser
than go around blowing
government buildings sky-high.
Yeah, well, as we said, sir,
this is just routine.
So routine it numbs the mind.
I've got my ag card and my papers
around here somewhere.
Help me look for 'em, will ya?
As we reported earlier,
a wild police pursuit ended in tragedy
with the death
of a 36-year-old female hostage.
This was the scene
west of Elko, Nevada, one hour ago...
Hey, Scully, take a look at this.
We want to warn our viewers
this footage is extremely graphic.
(reporter) The hostage is inside the car.
It appears that she's banging
her head against the window.
(anchorman) At this time, officials
are refusing to identify the woman
or to speculate on how she died. They
stress it was not the result of a gunshot.
A preliminary coroner's report
isn't expected for a day.
Meanwhile, residents of northern Nevada...
Thank you, Captain. That's no problem.
We'd be happy to help.
Mm-hm.
- We'll be happy to help what?
- See you soon.
- We're not going to Nevada.
- Come on, one quick side trip.
No. We have a whole new assignment.
Running down people that buy fertiliser?
This is bozo work.
This is the FBI equivalent of wearing
an orange jump suit and picking up trash.
They mean to humiliate us.
Look, Mulder, like it or not,
humiliated or not,
we're on domestic terrorism now.
And yes, this is a punishment.
But if we wanna get back, we have to
follow orders. We can't freelance.
You saw the news.
What did you make of that?
The obvious assumption is she was shot,
regardless of what the police say.
Maybe it was a sniper.
In the captain's words,
"She just sorta popped."
What about this guy who tried
to take her hostage - her husband?
Looked to me like he was trying
to warn the cops before she died.
The sun will rise in America tomorrow,
regardless of whether we're at a farm
investigating yet another
enormous pile of doo-doo.
We can be in and out in a day.
Nobody has to know.
(door clangs)
(tone)
Somebody! Please!
It's starting!
Somebody!
Why can't we see him?
Hopefully later. He pitched
quite a fit in his cell,
screamin' a bunch of nonsense
that we were gonna kill him like his wife.
- He's not a particularly stable individual.
- He may need medical attention.
He's getting it. Our doctor's with him now.
I mean, after whatever happened to his wife,
which I'd like to stress was not our fault,
we're not gonna take any chances.
Patrick Garland Crump of Montello, Nevada.
(Mulder) 40-year-old roofer,
no history of mental illness.
- No prior record.
- He's got one now.
That Barracuda he jacked
on the Utah state line?
He yanked some teenager out of the window,
threw his wife in the back and took off.
Excuse me.
What do you think?
I'm thinking, while we're here,
I might take a look at Mr Crump's wife.
I'm gonna stay here
and see if I can see Crump.
- Captain? Where's Montello?
- Little town right here.
So that's where it started.
That's Crump's home.
Then he headed east in this direction,
on the 5, about ten miles to the Utah border,
where he stole the car.
You got it.
But you caught up with him in Wells.
Where's that?
That's here. He started in this direction,
then all of a sudden he turned around
and he headed west to Wells. Why?
The former Vicky Jenkins Crump.
I'm hoping you can tell me what I'm
looking at, cos this is a new one on me.
There's no gunpowder residue.
No carbon stippling.
There seems to be no evidence
of an entry wound.
There is none. It's all exit.
But how that could be...
I'm finding fragments of petrous bone
embedded in the remaining portion
of the auditory canal.
I seem to be looking through to the
osseous labyrinth, or what's left of it.
It's almost like a little bomb
went off in her ear.
- May I?
- Please.
Seems to be some kind of tumefaction
within the lateral sinus.
(man) Can you give us a little room here?
He just went rammy on me. Accu-Check
is normal. We did a Narcan push.
He keeps getting worse.
IV beta-blocker and topical nitro.
I don't know if you're gonna
get to talk to this fella.
Five's a crowd, buddy.
(Siren)
(monitor beeping rapidly)
(beeping slows)
Something must have worked.
Heart rate's dropping.
BP's headed south.
- I don't understand. What'd you just do?
- Hell if I know. But I'll take it.
(cellphone ringing)
Come on, Mulder.
Hey, you, out! This lab is quarantined! Go!
- Mulder?
- Yeah?
Mulder, it's me. You know how
to pick 'em, I'll tell you that.
I have no idea what killed this woman,
but I assume it's communicable.
Yeah?
Another body was found outside of Montello.
Same apparent cause of death:
a massive aneurysmal rupture.
- Uh-huh.
- I've called the CDC. They're on their way.
But Patrick Crump may be infected,
so you need to quarantine him,
and make sure that anybody who has had
any contact with him is quarantined as well.
And that means you, Mulder. You're to
have no contact with him whatsoever.
Mulder?
Well, that's gonna be a little tough, Scully.
(Sirens)
Drive.
(cellphone rings)
- Where are they?
- Route 789, heading west.
We're keeping 'em in visual,
plus we're in phone contact.
Not to mention the strings we pulled
to keep this off local TV.
- Where are they going?
- Crump won't say.
Wherever it is, though,
he ain't getting there.
- Roadblock?
- East of Tuscarora.
- Nice, clean, remote space we can own.
- All right. I want the CDC on site.
I want the officers making the arrest to be
wearing level two anti-contamination suits.
I want the car decontaminated,
also Agent Mulder and Crump,
- and I want them quarantined separately.
- You got it.
Crump says that if we don't pull back
our escort, he's gonna shoot your partner.
Just leave me the hell alone!
Now!
How about if we just pull over
and let me out, too, huh?
- I must be crampin' your style.
- Just shut up.
It's you people. Figures.
- What figures?
- Shut up.
(cellphone rings)
- Damn.
- Hey! No!
No!
- That is so stupid, Crump. That is so stupid.
- Shut up!
You shut up and drive. You understand?
What the hell are you doing?
I'm composing a sonnet.
I'm slowing down for a light.
Go!
(car horns)
Stump'?
Is this what happened to your wife?
This same thing?
If you stop movin', you die?
I think I saw this movie.
Why didn't you tell anybody?
Why didn't you tell the police?
Sure.
I don't know how well you recall the last
30 seconds, but your life is in my hands,
- regardless of that gun.
- It's right here, boy.
Tell me everything.
That's the only way I can help.
- You people put me here!
- Shut up!
I'm guessin' we got two miles
before the roadblock.
- What roadblock? I got rid of the cops.
- Check your window.
Man, if we get stopped...
(police radio) Police should be advised
pursuit now headed west on 80.
14, come in.
14, be advised,
vehicle is headed your way.
(helicopter pilot) Subject turning off
east of your position and is heading north.
- Looks like he's gonna miss you.
- Say what?
- What's the report, Captain?
- They lost 'em.
They were last seen
on a forestry service road.
Our helicopter lost sight of 'em.
How did Crump know
to avoid the roadblock?
That's the question.
I was hoping your Agent Mulder would
manage to steer him toward it, but...
Maybe Mulder steered him away from it.
- Why would he do that?
- Maybe he knew something that we don't.
(man) Agent Scully? I've got
the cell filters from the second victim.
Anything?
So far I'm seeing no evidence
of infection in either victim.
So then we're in the clear?
No, no, not necessarily.
I mean, something killed these people.
(Cellphone)
- Scully.
- (woman) Agent Scully?
Please hold for Assistant Director Kersh.
- (sighs)
- (Kersh) Agent Scully.
- Yes, sir?
- How's southern Idaho?
Agent Scully? Southern Idaho?
Think carefully.
Sir, I am not currently in the state of Idaho.
No, you're not.
In the course of prosecuting
our assignment in Idaho,
Agent Mulder and I came across
a situation in Nevada,
which we both felt needed
our immediate attention.
I eagerly await your report.
In the meantime, agents
of our Las Vegas field office
will be available to assist you
in tracking down Agent Mulder.
Thank you, sir.
Oh, Agent Scully...
At this point, I want to see
him alive even more than you.
Can I see that for a minute?
- This man worked reading meters.
- Yes.
What if he read the meter
at Vicky Crump's place?
Crump? Crump, what else can you tell me
about what's happening to you?
Mr Crump.
You call me by my last name,
you say "Mr" in front of it.
- "Mr." Gotcha.
- Not Crump. Mr Crump.
I can think of something else
I'd like to call you.
I could put "Mr" in front
of that too, if you'd like.
What kind of name is Mulder anyway?
What is that, like... like Jewish?
Excuse me?
Jewish. It is, right?
It's Mr Mulder to you,
you peanut-pickin' bastard.
Mr Crump, what can you tell me
about what's ha...
Argh!
- What?
- You're goin'... the wrong way.
- What do you mean, it's the wrong way?
- Go this way!
I can't go... I can't go left.
There's only trees there.
Crump.
(Cfump moans)
(car horn)
Crump.
It's west, huh? West. You gotta head west.
It's like with your wife.
You took her and you headed west.
It's not just motion. It has to be
in one direction. Is that right?
What the hell happened to you?
OK. I want a thorough search,
with an eye to the usual disease vectors.
(man) You got it.
(dog barking)
I think we're witnessing
the same pathology here.
- We need to get a blood sample.
- Yeah. Let's go.
(man) Hold him!
Get him on his side!
Hold him down!
You gotta hold him still.
(Scully) I'm gonna sedate him.
- (Mulder) You woke up. Then what?
- We have been through this.
You woke up this morning,
but you didn't go to work. Why?
It was raining'. You don't shingle in the rain.
I was up at six readin' the paper.
What was your wife doing?
Cookin', man. Breakfast. She was just
puttin' breakfast on the table when, uh...
- You looked up.
- I looked up
and I saw that she had this nosebleed
she didn't even know she had.
- What caused it?
- What am I? I'm, like, Quincy?
How the hell should I know what caused it?
It just happened.
Ten, 15 minutes later,
she just... starts getting sick.
Says she got a headache that just
keeps gettin' worse and worse.
She starts... screamin'.
I didn't know what the hell to do.
I just, uh...
I got her in the truck
and was takin' her to the hospital.
But then it seemed like the faster
we went, the better she'd do.
Butjust as soon as I'd try
to slow down or stop...
I'm sorry about your wife.
Sure you are.
You and the rest of your Jew FBI.
- Cmmp“
- You think I don't know, huh?
You think I'm just some ignorant
pudknocker, don't you? But I get it, man!
I see what this is!
I am not sick and I do not have the flu.
Vicky and me were just some kinda...
government guinea pigs.
- You think the government did this?
- Hell, yeah. Who else?
You see it all the time on the TV.
They're droppin' Agent Orange.
They're puttin' radiation
in little retarded kids' gonads.
You sons of bitches sneakin'
around my woods at night.
I seen you. You think I don't know?
On behalf of the international Jewish
conspiracy, I need to inform you
that we're... almost out of gas.
(man) The trailer looks clean.
No readily apparent vectors.
Dogs, housewives... whatever
this thing is, it doesn't discriminate.
There are zoonotic pathogens
which spread among species.
Look at that.
The Crumps have a neighbour.
(knocking)
Hello?
Doctor.
(screams)
Oh, no... It's OK, ma'am.
- Who are you?
- It's all right. Sorry.
Go away! Go away!
(mumbles)
It's OK... It's OK.
(Mulder) OK, Crump,
we got about one more mile.
I'll make it fast. You ready?
Here goes nothin'.
Turn on the pump!
Number four... three!
Number three! Turn it on!
You gotta pay before you pump, buddy.
Hey! Dammit, that's my car! Where in
the hell do you think you're going?
Dammit, stop!
Stop!
(elderly woman mumbling)
(woman) We'll take care of you.
Watch your step.
We just have to examine you...
One deaf woman survives unscathed
while everything else around her dies.
Why?
Wait. What are you doing?
The pathology of this thing...
it affects the inner ear.
And this area right here is ground zero.
What if what we're looking for
is some kind of a sound?
Seriously?
(cellphone rings)
- Scully.
- It's Van Gelder.
I don't know what your partner's thinking.
Not only is he actively evading
my officers, now he's stolen a car.
- Come again?
- You heard right.
He left behind a crazy note addressed to you.
- You there?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Read it to me.
"Crump's sick. Will die if stopped."
"Same as wife. Must head west
to keep alive. No roadblocks..."
Exclamation point.
- This make any sense to you?
- Take him at his word. Let him through.
Let him through?
Look, no of fence, Agent Scully,
but how about you running it by your
superiors? I think they'll say different.
I'll take that under advisement.
Agent Scully, you're breaking up...
(Static)
Faster.
- I'm doing 70.
- You gotta go faster. It's getting worse.
Yeah. Yeah, that's good. OK.
Hey, uh...
The Jew stuff...
No of fence.
I mean, a man can't help who he's born to.
That was an apology, right?
Gee, I don't know if I can see to drive,
my eyes are tearin' up so bad.
Whatever, man.
Why you doin' this?
- Why am I doin' what?
- This.
It's not in your interest
to make me question that.
How do I know you ain't doin'
exactly what they want you to? Hm?
Drivin' me all around creation, experimentin'
on me. How do I know it ain't that?
I guess you don't.
I ain't sayin' you are. I'm just
saying it's no way to treat a man.
Take away his dignity like that.
It ain't right.
Betterjust to kill him.
That's all I'm sayin'.
You gotta stay alive to stick it to the
government. If you die, they're off the hook.
Am I right?
- Huh?
- You're right. You're damn straight.
We'll figure this out.
Better figure quick. We're runnin' out of west.
Lieutenant Breil? My name is Dana Scully.
I called regarding the electrical equipment
the navy maintains in Montello.
I don't know if there's miscommunication
between you and your Washington office...
My Washington office?
I was under the impression I'd explained
this to the FCC's satisfaction.
I'm... I'm so sorry to make you
run through it again, uh...
for my official report to the FCC.
At 6.17 yesterday morning, during a test
of our ground conduction radio system,
a situation arose in which our equipment
experienced a brief power surge.
That's what interrupted television
reception in the four-state area.
Steps have been taken to ensure
this won't happen again.
The ground conduction radio,
that would be Project Seafarer?
The specifics of what we do are classified.
Sure. Sure.
Would you happen to know what effect
such a surge might have on an organism?
Say, um... say a human being?
- Theoretically speaking.
- Theoretically speaking...
that's classified as well, ma'am.
- Cmmp
- Mr Crump.
Mr Crump.
What is it, Mr Mulder?
Mulder. Are you OK?
Yeah, aside from cellphone withdrawal,
and I gotta pee. Where are you?
I'm about to board a Justice Department
jet. Hopefully, I'll overshoot you.
- Headed where'?
- I don't know. You tell me.
I'm guessing wherever Route 36 ends,
but we can't stop and I'm kind of
at a loss as to what to do next.
I think I have a loose theory
as to what caused this.
- Well, lay it on me.
- OK.
You know what ELF waves are?
Extremely low frequency
radio transmissions?
Use an antenna, like, 50 miles long.
The military uses it to communicate with
the Trident submarines - Project Seafarer.
Seafarer has an antenna array stretching
beneath the edge of Crump's property.
Now, ELF fields have been shown to produce
biological effects in human tissue,
inducing electrical currents,
altering chemical reactions.
As a potential weapons application,
it's referred to as electrical nerve gas,
or may be behind the Taos Hum.
What if some overload,
some hum from this system,
could somehow match the resonant
frequency of the human skull?
I mean, what if it could induce a like hum
that could somehow exert a rising pressure
on the inner ear, shattering it?
With constant movement ameliorating
that pressure, making it bearable?
- But why only westward movement?
- I don't know, Mulder. I don't know. I mean...
Maybe it follows certain lines of force,
electrical or magnetic.
But the big question, Scully,
is what do we do about it?
I think I know, Mulder, but it's nothing
that Mr Crump is gonna like.
We'll be there.
What?
Whether they did this to you intentionally
or not, you were right. They did it to you.
So what do we... what do we do?
Your one chance is that we meet my partner
at the end of the highway.
There she will insert a large-bore needle
into your inner ear,
hopefully relieving the pressure.
When we get there, she'll have to work fast.
She'll only have one chance.
She's not gonna be able to use anaesthetic.
And it will probably leave you deaf.
But I'll live, right?
Well... Well, that's what it's all about.
All right, man. Let's do it.
Mr Mulder, could you
go a little faster, please?
- Just a little more is all I need.
- Sure.
Just a little bit faster.
Get ready!
(Kersh) Justice Department jet:
2.6 turbine hours round trip
at $1400 an hour.
Car rental. Over-mileage,
out-of-state use penalties: $346.
Compensation to one Walter R Duncan
for unauthorised use
of his 1968 Caprice station wagon: $500.
- Why don't you bill me?
- I'll bill your partner instead.
You two obviously relish the role of martyr.
OK, so are we done here?
Back to the bozo work,
investigating huge piles of manure?
You can always quit.
Sir, Agent Mulder has been through a lot.
You apologise for him a lot.
I've noticed that about you.
I'm not apologising for this.
Because of his work, the DOD are shutting
down their antenna array in Nevada.
- Our participation has saved lives.
- I don't see you proving that.
The Department of Defense
admits no culpability.
Furthermore, they say the closing
of their facility was coincidental.
Right.
Don't misunderstand me, Agent.
I don't care if you two saved
a school bus full of doe-eyed urchins
on their way to Sunday bible camp.
You no longer investigate X-Files.
You are done.
And the sooner you and Mulder come to
recognise that, the better for both of you.
Big piles of manure.
Visiontext Subtitles: Yasmin Rammohan
(Child) I made this!