The malfunction cut off power
to rural parts of Kroner County.
Up next, the amazing story
of two giant pandas in love.
But first, let's check in with
Holman Hardt and the weather.
Still no rain in sight for the Kroner Hills region
as another winter storm passes south of us.
I'll have all the numbers
and my five-day forecast right after this.
(door closes)
Hey, baby, you're home early!
Sheila, we got a really big problem here.
What in the hell were you thinkin'?
Happy Valentine's Day.
We made a deal.
We agreed to keep
the engagement secret until I said so.
I know, but I just wanted
everybody in town to know
why I've been so happy
the last few months.
...yet another bone-dry day.
The current temperature in Kroner is
45 degrees, with lows tonight around 40.
I know business is slow, but we can't stop
living just cos it hasn't rained in a spell.
Maybe we should just
call off the engagement.
Don't do this, not today.
It'll rain soon. I can feel it!
I just need time to think.
Oh, look at that. And you
wonder why your ass is so big.
(mimicking) "It'll rain soon. I can feel it."
(switches on radio)
(flips through stations)
What I got they used to call the blues
Nothin' is really wrong
Feelin' like I don't belong
Walkin' around
(sings along) Some kind of lonely clown
Rainy days and Mondays
always get me down
Funny but it seems
I always wind up here with you
Nice to know somebody loves me
Funny, but it seems that
it's the only thing to do
- Run and find the one...
- I'll be damned!
What I feel has come and gone...
Yee-ha!
Ow!
We know what it's all about
Hangin' around
Nothin' to do but frown
Rainy days and Mondays
always get me down
Hangin' around
Nothin' to do but frown
Rainy days and Mondays
always get me down
(marching band)
Don't look at me. This was your idea.
Agent Mulder, welcome to Kroner.
I'm Jim Gilmore, the mayor.
We spoke on the phone. If I'd known
you were bringin' the missis,
- I'd have arranged fancier accommodation.
- I'm Agent Scully, Mulder's partner.
I'm sure the accommodation will be just fine.
Apologies, ma'am.
We appreciate you flying out here
to help solve our crisis.
I'd hoped for a bigger welcome, but, well...
OK, Rhonda, that's enough.
Go find your momma.
(switches music off)
Uh, sir, you mentioned a crisis.
Agent Mulder has been a little vague
as to the specifics of this crisis.
Well, it's all around us.
Runted crops, field fires, bankruptcies.
The drought is destroyin' people's lives.
It's wrong for a single man
to prosper at the expense of others.
A single man?
Daryl Mootz.
He's a local fella, chargin' people for rain.
- You mean cloud seeding?
- The hell I do.
He shows up at a farm, does his
dog-and- pony act, and the heavens weep.
Well, sir, if this man Mootz could,
in fact, somehow produce rain,
then what's the crime?
I believe Daryl's causin' the drought
so he can charge folks for the rain.
This is what you told Agent Mulder
when you spoke earlier?
Yes, ma'am.
He seemed real eager to help us.
Come on, Scully. You act
like I intentionally misled you.
Over the past 30 years,
this town's had more tornadoes,
heat waves and hailstorms than
any other town in the country. It's like...
ground zero for extreme weather.
A man controlling the weather.
If that's true, if Daryl Mootz
is controlling the weather for profit,
then that is a crime
that should be investigated.
I see the vacant buildings. I see the signs.
These people are scared. But there have
always been droughts and natural disasters,
and people always look for a scapegoat.
Yeah, but how many scapegoats
lease office space?
(news on TV)
Agents Mulder and Scully, FBI.
We're looking for Daryl Mootz.
(whispers) One second.
Yes, ma'am. Appendix C, that's right.
I need a six-pack of beer,
a carton of Morley Lights,
and a big bowl of jellybeans.
And can you pick out all the green ones?
Cos he don't like the green ones.
You're welcome.
Now, what can I do for the FBI?
We want to see the king.
I'm sorry, he's out of state
till this afternoon on business.
When you say on business,
you mean he's making it rain?
Uh-huh. He's just across
the state line. Nebraska.
- Town of Wymore.
- If we could get a list of all the people
who have employed his services,
it would be helpful.
I don't understand. Has he...?
Don't y'all need a warrant or
a subpoena or something like that?
We usually just say "please".
What are you investigating Daryl for?
He's a hero in this community.
You actually believe that he makes it rain?
I know it to be fact.
He saved my daddy's farm.
How dare you people!
The only rain in the area
is localised up around Wymore.
See? Daryl's making that rain.
Is it possible he could have
followed it up there?
Here's your damn client list.
You'll see: every one a satisfied customer.
This TV station. Is that far from here?
Oh! We were beginning to worry
that you wouldn't make it.
This your first time in a TV studio?
How exciting.
I couldn't be happier for the two of you.
I'm not sure...
They're here. The Gundersons are here.
Holman, I'd like to introduce you
to the Gundersons.
Congratulations. I hope you have
a truly romantic getaway.
Aren't you glad you watch
Channel 5 Weather?
We're Agents Mulder and Scully.
We're with the FBI.
FBI? Oh, my goodness. I thought you were
the "Watch the Weather and Win"
contest winners.
See, we haven't had any rain in months,
and people tend to blame the messenger.
Oh, there's the Gundersons. Over here!
It's like looking in a mirror.
When I saw the pair of you, I thought you
were smartly dressed for a farm couple.
Make yourselves at home.
From what I've read, Kroner's had more
than its fair share of unusual weather.
We certainly have.
To you, Kroner must seem
small and simple,
but through the eyes of meteorology -
low-pressure systems,
storm fronts, tornado watches -
Kroner is sophisticated, complex,
and, well...
sexy.
Frankly, I can't imagine a more
exciting place to be a meteorologist.
Mr Hardt, what can you tell us
about Daryl Mootz?
Oh, the mayor called you in, didn't he?
He thinks Daryl's causing the drought.
- You don't think he's responsible.
- Of course not.
A huge high-pressure system
is the primary culprit.
There's no evidence
to suggest that Daryl, or any man,
can be held accountable for our predicament.
- Thank you. Can we go now?
- No. Uh, what about the rain?
That's a more... clouded issue,
if you'll excuse my pun.
I have a list of over 40 names here.
People in four different counties who claim
that Daryl Mootz has made it rain for them.
I went to high school with Daryl.
Different social circles, and...
Frankly, he's about the last man
I would give credit to for anything...
I hear a big "but" coming.
Daryl appears to be the real deal.
I can't explain it, but...
where he wanders, showers follow.
Look at the desperation on their faces.
They're ready to believe anything.
According to his schedule,
the king should have been here by now.
(man) Here he comes!
(Daryl) Oh, isn't that sweet?
Man, what could we use around here,
a little rain? (laughs)
Oh, look at this. Ah.
Take these, will you, somebody?
Ahh. Ah.
That is the wrong damn boot now,
isn't it, hon?
Be a good girl and go on
and get me the red snakeskin.
Well, lookie here.
The FBI.
We just came to see the show.
I guess we're a little early.
O ye of little faith.
That truck out there of mine
is a whole lot faster than my rain clouds.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
- How do you explain your unique ability?
- I don't.
It's complicated.
Try me. I watch The Weather Channel.
If you're wondering, did I ask for this gift,
no, sir, I did not.
No more than I asked to lose this here limb.
But I should have expected it.
And I'll tell you why.
Because I come from
a long line of healin' people.
I'm a spiritual man in touch
with the really real.
The... the unseen real.
(instrumental rock)
And I... am 1/64th Cherokee.
And I can summon up my ancestors
to bring water to this thirsty land.
Yeah!
- Mulder, what are we doing here?
- This is not without historical precedent.
The Old West was full of men
who claimed to be rainmakers.
- The Pueblo Indians even had a rain dance.
- Mulder, that is not a rain dance.
My Irish Aunt Olive has more
Cherokee in her than Daryl Mootz.
Does that look like a man
who can control the weather?
(thunderclap)
(excited yelling)
Yeah!
Are we still going to the reunion
together on Friday?
Absolutely. Social event of the decade.
Hard to believe it's been 20 years
since we finished high school.
Where did the time go?
What were those FBI people looking for?
They were asking questions about Daryl.
About making it rain.
I wish they'd just go back to wherever
they came from and leave him alone.
You don't still love him, do you?
I can't believe you still care about him
after the way he treated you.
- I know.
- He never loved you, Sheila.
All he cared about was your money,
and as soon as he got some of his own...
He left. I know.
But I think he used to love me.
There are other men who'll love you more.
FBI, my Lord.
I don't think I'll be able to sleep,
knowin' they're pokin' around.
(shutters banging)
(sighs)
(blinds clattering)
(cow moos)
(man) Unless you want to get covered
in hamburger, you should step outside.
(chain saw)
Oh, Miss, we moved your
boyfriend's things into your room.
He's my partner,
and we prefer separate rooms.
Old-fashioned, are you, huh?
We're booked solid with
the high-school reunion. Take it or leave it.
We can just butterfly it.
I've got my kit over in the car.
I don't think it's a coincidence
that a cow gets hurled at me
just as we're down here
investigating the weather.
- Did they check you for head trauma?
- That cow had my name on it.
Agent Mulder, are you all right?
I feel terrible. If there's anything
I can do, please don't hesitate.
Perhaps there is. Would you
please reassure Agent Mulder
that this cow incident was,
in fact, a natural phenomenon?
With pleasure.
I believe that a mini-twister
picked that poor creature up,
lifted it about 12,000 feet,
where the air cooled, and, uh...
I'm just grateful
you weren't hurt any worse.
(Sheila) Excuse me.
- You shouldn't be here.
- Holman, don't make this any harder.
It's my fault. I did it.
I'm so sorry. I didn't mean for this to happen.
- It's not something that I can control.
- Are you saying you're responsible for...
I murdered that poor cow!
Holman just explained to us that
a mini-twister is what caused the accident.
He's just being sweet, covering for me.
He knows the truth.
This isn't the first time
something like this happened.
The night of my senior prom,
a tornado demolished our high school.
(screaming)
And then, on my wedding day,
a day I'd always dreamed about,
the ceremony was outdoors
on the 4th of July weekend.
It snowed six inches.
Three years later, my husband ran off
with some gal from the phone company,
and on the day
that our divorce was finalised,
I stepped out of the courthouse, and...
You know how you... you can see
shapes in those big fluffy clouds?
Well...
I swear that every cloud in that
big, blue sky was a face laughing at me.
That was about 10 years ago,
and that was the last time it happened
until last night.
- What's your connection to Daryl Mootz?
- Well, we used to be engaged.
You two were engaged?
Yeah, about six months ago,
and, uh, we had a fight and he took a drive,
and... and a freak hailstorm cost him his leg.
And ever since then,
the rain's been following him.
- Am I under arrest?
- No.
Without a doubt, you're not
responsible for any of that weather.
Oh. But...
Agent Scully and I specialise
in these types of cases.
And although you may have had
some bad luck, you didn't cause any of it.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, yeah. I'm sure.
- Scully, do you have any doubts?
- No. No doubts.
It's fine.
I really wanna believe you.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
- That hailstorm didn't cause Daryl's crash.
- What are you talking about?
The weather was bad, but he
was drunk and drivin' too fast.
Drunk? I never heard that.
We all felt that Daryl losing his leg
was punishment enough.
People don't realise how hard a work this is.
I mean, sure, it looks like
I'm just sittin' here, but...
my powers of concentration are...
Oh, yeah. Oh, right there. Yeah.
Yeah, you're worth every penny.
- What was I sayin'?
- Powers of concentration?
- Right.
My brain's functionin' on
something like 14 different levels,
taking in a whole bunch of variables,
like wind velocity and humidity and...
Daryl.
- Do you hear that?
- Hear what?
The rain stopped.
Uh-oh.
(door opens)
- Next flight out is 10am.
- Look at this, Scully.
September 20th, 1991.
It rained rose petals for nearly an hour.
We're going home.
The rain stopped this afternoon.
Daryl Mootz is being sued
by about 50 people. There's no case.
You told Sheila that she
wasn't controlling the weather.
She's not. Neither is Daryl.
But check this out:
On the same day that it rained rose petals...
"lrene Hardt, beloved wife and devoted
mother, passed away yesterday afternoon."
"She's survived by one son,
Holman Hardt."
- You're saying Holman...
- Is manufacturing the weather.
Did you see his relief when
he learned Daryl was drunk?
I've been doing some checking.
Holman Hardt has been hospitalised
five times with nervous exhaustion,
each time coinciding with
a major meteorological event.
It is still a huge leap to say that
he's manufacturing the weather.
Most people admit the weather plays
a significant role in the way they feel.
- There's even that disorder.
- SAD: seasonal affective disorder.
Who's to say it doesn't work both ways? That
the way someone feels can affect the weather.
That the weather is somehow
an expression of Holman Hardt's feelings.
Or better still, the feelings
that he's not expressing.
I've tried to say this a thousand times,
tried to express the...
fire that burns inside this humble exterior.
Sheila, you're the reason I remained
in this town all these years.
(Phone)
I wake up each day knowing...
- Hello?
- Holman, it's me. Working late?
Sheila, hi. Yeah, um...
I was just thinking about you.
I'm looking forward
to the reunion tomorrow night.
- Me too.
- You sound in a good mood.
I am, Holman, and it's all because of you.
I want you to know that I've been thinking
about what you said about Daryl yesterday,
- and I realised that you were right.
- I was?
Yes, you were, and I am so over him.
Daryl who? That's what I say.
I realised that I've been chasing
the wrong kind of guy.
I need someone who I can talk to.
I need someone who I can feel safe with.
I can't tell you what that means to me.
Holman, I want to ask you something,
and I hope that we can keep it
our secret for the time being.
Of course, Sheila. Anything.
Well, what do you think of Agent Mulder?
(thunder)
(knocks)
Hey, Holman.
- Agent Mulder.
- I've come to say goodbye.
- You're leaving?
- Yeah.
But I want you to get some help
before you kill somebody.
- What do you mean?
- You know what I mean.
You're not just a weatherman.
You're the weatherman.
You're the person who's
affecting the weather.
If I could control the weather, don't you
think I'd make it rain, and end this drought?
I don't think you do it on purpose.
I think you bottle up your emotions -
anger, grief, love or whatever -
and then as a response it rains
or hails or there's a flying cow.
- That poor animal.
- Well, whatever it is, you gotta let it out.
I can't.
Yeah, you can.
It's Sheila, isn't it? You love her.
You've always loved her.
That, uh, tornado at the high school.
That was you, wasn't it?
The night of our senior prom, I, uh...
accidentally stumbled upon
her and her boyfriend...
in flagrante delicto.
And the next thing you know...
And you've never told her the way you feel?
How could a frog tell a swan
that he loves her?
Well, you'd better tell her,
or you're gonna kill somebody.
- You gotta help me.
- I got a plane to catch.
You can't go.
If you don't help me, who will?
- I am meeting my partner at the airport.
- (cell phone rings)
- Mulder.
- (Scully) Mulder, it's me.
- I'm on my way.
- I'm not so sure.
Have you looked outside lately?
It's pea soup.
- Our plane can't take off until this fog lifts.
- Fog'?
Holman!
- Holman?
- Yeah, he wants advice. Dating advice.
- Dating advice? From whom?
- Yours truly.
Hello? Hey, Scully?
- Scully, are you there?
- I heard you.
Mulder, when was the last time
you went on a date?
I will talk to you later.
The blind leading the blind.
This red number?
Daryl, you're like one of
those tragic rock stars.
You know, like Jim Morrison or Kurt Cobain.
You just shine too bright for too short a time.
We'll tell our kids all about it.
Kids? I can't afford kids.
If I don't come up with a lot of cash pronto,
I am in deep doo-doo.
Dairy Queen'll take me back.
I get almost $6 an hour.
Sh! I'm thinkin'.
- There's got to be somebody...
- We'll get the money, baby.
- Sheila.
- What about her?
Cindy...
You have been real sweet and all,
but I think we can use some time apart.
- What? Are you breakin' up with me?
- Nothin' personal.
(Holman) I've been envious of men
like you my whole life.
Based on your physical bearing,
I'd assumed you were more experienced.
You spend every day with Agent Scully,
a beautiful, enchanting woman.
You mean you two never, uh...?
I confess I find that shocking. l...
I've seen how you two gaze at one another.
This is about you, Holman.
I'm here to help you.
I'm perfectly happy with
my friendship with Agent Scully.
So, your theory is I walk in there, tell her
I love her, and the drought will end?
Just tell her how you feel.
And Holman? I do not gaze at Scully.
_ Hey-
I can't find my notes for my... presentation.
There they are.
- You got a minute?
- For you, always.
Are you excited about the reunion tonight?
Of course.
- You're busy. We can talk later.
- Oh, what is it?
L.-
I love you.
I love you, too.
Holman, what's wrong?
(rainfall)
- (woman) Is that rain? Oh, my God! It is!
- (thunder)
(woman) It's raining!
Well?
Good afternoon, Agent Mulder.
See you tonight, Holman.
Oh, you did it.
No, you did it.
- What are you talking about?
- She said that she loves me,
but that she's in love with you.
- What do you mean, there's somebody else?
- Daryl!
- Just tell me who it is.
- Let me go!
Hey!
Hey, Daryl. Cut it out, man.
Him?
This is the guy?
- Well, what's he got that I ain't got?
- A job.
A way with words. Intelligence, good looks.
Good-lookin'? I'll show you good-lookin'!
- Daryl, no! Not his face!
- Daryl...
Don't you hit him in the face!
Oh, good, pick on a cripple.
You'll hear from my lawyer.
- You deserve a big reward.
- No.
Mulder, the fog has lifted,
and if you're ready, the plane is waiting.
Scully, do you know
anything about weather radar?
- A bit. Why?
- What does red mean?
Thunderstorms, I think.
Looks like we won't
be able to catch our plane.
("Rock the Boat" by Hues Corporation)
Said I'd like to know where
you got the notion
- To rock the boat
- Don't rock the boat, baby
- Rock the boat
- Don't tip the boat over
- Don't rock the boat, baby
Rock the boat
Up to now we sailed through every storm
- (thunder)
- I've always had your tender lips
To keep me warm
Oh, I need to have the strength
that flows from you
Don't let me drift away, my dear
When love can see me through
Seven inches in the past six hours.
The National Weather Service issued
a flash-flood warning for the county.
- Mulder, are you sure he's here?
- If she's here, he'll be here.
So I'd like to know where
you got the notion
Said I'd like to know where
So I'd like to know where
you got the notion
Said I'd like to know where
- Come on, make it stop.
- This is your fault, not mine.
- My fault?
- You were kissing her.
Oh, look who's here.
Some of my favourite people.
Old friends, and new ones.
- You look very lovely.
- Thank you.
You look handsome. Both of you.
- ("The Things We Do For Love")
- Oh, I love this song.
Agent Mulder, care to dance?
Holman was just telling us
that he wanted to dance.
Yes, he was.
- I would be honoured.
- OK.
Tell her, Holman.
You lay your bets
and then you pay the price...
What was that Agent Mulder said?
Tell me what?
Oh, it's... no big deal.
We tell each other everything, don't we?
Well...
When I stopped by
your office this afternoon...
- I said that...
- When you said you loved me...
What I meant to say...
What I wanted you to understand...
is that I'm in love with you.
I've loved you since high school.
Ooh, you made me love you
Ooh, you've got a way
(thunder)
I'll build the ark, you gather the animals.
I was kidding.
Sheila.
My partner has a theory,
and even though I don't share his belief,
I feel that given the circumstances,
you should hear his theory,
because it involves you and Holman.
Agent Mulder believes
that the drought, this storm,
this bizarre set of weather conditions
that have plagued you over the years,
are... are caused by Holman.
Specifically, that... that his emotions
are somehow manifesting
themselves in the weather.
And Agent Mulder
believes that Holman is...
unwittingly destroying this town
because of his unspoken love for you.
- You love him, don't you?
- What?
You're jealous that Mulder
and I have a special connection,
- and you're trying to divert me to Holman.
- What?
It is good to be the king!
(laughs)
Where's Sheila?
- Where's your leg?
- Cindy took it.
Said I'd have to crawl back to her.
Now, where's Sheila?
Not even a kiss?
Trust me, the man knows how to kiss.
I've just never thought of Holman
that way, you know?
He's my closest friend.
And to not even suspect.
Well, it seems to me
that the best relationships, the ones that last,
are frequently the ones
that are rooted in friendship.
You know, one day you look at the person,
and you see something more
than you did the night before.
Like a switch has been flicked somewhere.
And the person who was just a friend is
suddenly the only person
you can ever imagine yourself with.
The storm drains are filling up.
Let's get outta here.
I'll teach you to mess with my woman!
- (woman) God, Daryl!
- If I had two legs, I'd kick your...
I called the police.
You might want to look at the king,
make sure he's all right.
Whatever happened to Sheila?
Is it true? That you make the weather?
Cos of me?
The tornado in high school?
- Snow at my wedding?
- I'm so sorry.
- Daryl's rain?
- I can't explain the logic of it.
Yes. Some strange manifestation of guilt.
Even this rain? Because you love me?
Because I love you.
That is the most romantic thing
I've ever heard.
(cheering)
Somewhere over the rainbow
Way up high
- I'm sorry, baby.
- Me too.
I brought you a leg.
Why are you so good to me, honey?
Over the rainbow
Skies are blue
And the dreams that you dare to dream
Really do come true...
- I didn't know reunions could be so...
- Wet?
Well, how'd it go?
You should try it sometime.
Sheila?
That's where you'll find me
I can't imagine
a more beautiful day than today...
Somewhere over the rainbow
(baby cries)
You're a chip off the old block. Yes, you are!
Yes, you are!
Why, oh, Why
Can't I?
Visiontext Subtitles: Karin Baker
(Child) I made this!