(British man) Easy. Steady up!
Hold on, mates. He's almost up.
That's it. Give him a big pull.
That's it. Don't drop him now. Come on.
Pull him over. Put your backs into it.
Come on!
- (man #2) Pick him up. Wakey wakey!
- (Mulder coughs and splutters)
(man #3) There he goes. Lots of life in him.
Give it up, matey. Good for ya.
That's what you get for your trouble.
(man #4) Maybe he's just taken a long swim.
(man #5) Yeah, or a short flight.
Are you an airman, mate?
(man #1) No, he's not dressed as an airman.
(man #3) What kind of uniform is that, then?
Sprechen Sie Deutsch, ja?
I say he's a rat and we throw him
overboard like a rat.
Yeah.
(man #5) Right. Let's give him the heave-ho.
(Mulder) Hey.
How's about another dip
in the Atlantic? Dirty Jerry.
Yeah. Even the sharks won't eat him.
Oi! What you got to say for yourself,
Jerry, before we throw you back in?
- My name's not Jerry.
- What's that? Eh?
My name's Mulder. Fox Mulder.
- (man #3) Is that a name? Mulder?
- I got ID in my pocket.
"Fox Mulder, Federal Bureau
of investigations."
- Sorry. Never heard of it.
- Never heard of it?
- I'll tell you what we do with foxes.
- You've never heard of the FBI?
- (man #4) Why don't you shut it, Jerry?
- (Mulder) Where are you taking me?
- (man #3) Where'd you get that accent?
- (man #4) In the Fuhrer's Secret Service.
(Mulder) What do you mean'?
(man #3) I say cut him and
see what colour he bleeds.
- Dirty Jerry!
- Deutschland Uber alles.
(Spits)
- Deutschland Uber alles? Wait a second.
- Oi!
How's about you shove
a cork in it, mate? All right?
Aye? What's this about?
We found him in the water, sir. Don't know
nothing about him. I think he's a German.
Bring the prisoner in my room.
Friend or foe?
Uh...
- What?
- To what flag do you pledge allegiance?
I think there's been a mistake.
I think the mistake is mine.
- Speak the truth.
- This is the Queen Anne?
- Aye.
- Hey, that's enough of that.
- I came looking for this ship.
- Say the word. I'll make him first.
- Wait. I think I can explain what's going on.
- It's a ruse, Captain.
- What's our current position?
- Cut the spy up.
No, I'll tell you. We're two degrees
above the 30th parallel.
Sargasso Sea. Just above
the tropic of Cancer.
64° west by southwest,
off the Plantagenet Bank.
60 miles south-southwest off Bermuda. How
would I know that if I'd been in the water?
Aye. That's a damn good question, lad.
I'm waiting for a damn good answer.
Tell me I'm wrong.
Tell me you haven't been
able to get accurate compass readings.
It's because you've been caught
in something called the Devil's Triangle.
I can show you.
It goes from Bermuda down
to Puerto Rico, back up to Florida.
The Queen Anne is stuck here
on the eastern edge.
You've been caught in some kind of
time warp, some kind of limbo dimension,
and now you've popped out
the other side into 1998.
- 1998?
- This man is mad.
- Let him tell it to the fishes.
- I'm done foolin' about. There's a war on.
And in it or no, I don't plan to lose me mind,
nor me ship, to the likes of a jackal like you.
Well, you can relax. There's no war.
The world is at peace.
There's a little trouble at our White House,
but that'll blow over, so to speak.
Peace? It's September 3, 1939, man.
Hitler has entered Poland. We've been
boarded by his goose-stepping hooligans,
so don't speak to me of peace, lad.
Tell Mother England.
No, it's not September 3.
It's November 16. Look.
- Excuse me, Captain.
- Aye.
Sir, the Germans, sir.
They've taken control of the bridge.
Steering a course for their homeland.
Not on the watch of Captain
Yip Harburg, they're not.
Lock the prisoner up in here.
It's OK. The war is over.
Let 'em take you to Germany.
They make nice cars.
This is unbelievable.
(radio crackles)
Mayday. Mayday. This is Special Agent
Fox Mulder with the FBI.
I'm on the SS Queen Anne.
Ship in distress. Mayday. Mayday.
(on radio) ..British ambassador in Berlin
handed the German government a final note
stating that unless we heard from them
that they were prepared at once
to withdraw their troops from Poland,
a state of war would exist between us.
No such undertaking has been received.
Consequently, as of today, September 3,
1939, this country is at war with Germany.
Oh, sh...
(German voices)
(German accent) Hello? Hello?
Hello?
(radio) ..closing places of entertainment.
All cinemas, theatres and other places of
entertainment are to be closed immediately
until further notice.
The evacuation of British children
is going on smoothly and efficiently.
The Ministry of Health says...
("Bei mir bist du schdn"
by the Andrews Sisters)
Please let me explain
"Bei mir bist du schdn"
means you're grand
Bei mir bist du schén
Again I'll explain
It means you're the fairest in the land
What the hell is goin' on?
Spender?
Even say wunderbar
Each language only helps me
tell you how grand you are
Ri di
Ri di, ri di
Ri di, ri di, ri di
- Hey!
- (German voices)
(German soldier) He, hast du was gefunden?
Bleib doch stehen! H6rst du nicht?
Umdrehen! Hast du was gefunden?
Warten Sie mal! Halt! Stehen bleiben!
Halt!
Hier ist er nicht! ZurUck!
(female singer and big band
perform "Jeepers Creepers")
When your eyes look into mine
Jeepers creepers
Where'd you get those peepers?
Gosh, oh, git up
How'd they get so lit up?
Hey.
Jeepers creepers
Where'd you get those peepers?
Excuse me.
Scully.
Get your Nazi paws off me
before you get one in the kisser.
No, it's me: Mulder.
You speak English? Want to see
the stars on the American flag?
- I'm not a Nazi.
- Oh, sure. You just look like one, right?
- I had to steal this uniform. Scully...
- Hierist der Mann, den Sie wollen!
(gunfire)
Hénde hoch! Hénde hoch!
He said put your hands up.
You see? I told you.
Jeepers creepers
You're all big men now,
but wait until you get to Russia.
I hope you fellas like the cold.
Hold still!
Hast GIUck,
dass wir dich nicht sofort abknallen.
- Same to you, Adolf.
- Schnauze!
Bringen Sie dieses Schiff
auf Fahrtrichtung Deutschland
oder wir schaffen Sie vom Steuer weg.
Verstanden?
I'll not give up this ship.
- Zeig ihm, was ich meine.
- Aye, you can put me down, man.
But I'll not let go of this wheel.
So till we meet in hell...
ErschieB ihn.
You.
Wer ist dieser Mann?
Er hat einen meiner Leute
zusammengeschlagen
und seine Uniform gestohlen. Er ist Spion.
W0 sind die Waffen versteckt?
- No sprechen.
- Die Waffen haben Sie an Bord, nicht?
I don't speak Nazi.
ErschieB ihn auch.
Wait a minute. Why are you shooting me?
Why are you killing me? What have I done?
I don't understand what you're asking me.
Halt! Nicht schieBen!
Dieser Mann ist ein Amerikaner. Oder
wollen Sie mehr Leute am Krieg beteiligen?
Bring ihn nach unten. Bring alle nach unten.
Skinner? Where are they taking me?
Help me, Skinner!
What are you guys doing here?
- Mulder's in trouble.
- What do you mean?
- Let's take a walk.
- OK. Where are we going?
- The walls have ears.
- I have ears. Tell me what's going on.
- Mulder's disappeared.
- From where?
From the National Reconnaissance Office's
Lacrosse mid-latitude imaging
radar satellite.
- What am I looking at?
- A whole lot of nothin'.
We got that 45 minutes ago
off the NRO satellite
which today sent a picture of a ship
which inexplicably appeared in the Atlantic.
The SS Queen Anne, which, by all accounts,
vanished over 60 years ago.
The British luxury liner.
- Right.
- It was torpedoed by a German U-boat.
- That's one story.
- There's another?
Though her exact position was
kept a secret for fear of spies
it's thought she was just south of the
Plantagenet Bank when she went missing.
Less than 60 feet of water,
yet she was never found.
- So she just disappeared?
- Into the Bermuda Triangle.
And reappeared this morning
at 6.49am Eastern Standard Time.
Impossible.
- The satellite can't lie.
- It's blank.
We gave the original images
to Mulder for navigational aids.
- He was in a hurry.
- To get where?
- Out to the Queen Anne before anyone else.
- He's gone out here?
He went to Bermuda and
he chartered a powerboat.
- We tracked him on the satellite.
- Until the storm obscured transmissions.
- That's what you have.
- What happened?
We can't know without alternative
tracking data, which is why we're here.
Without data we can only hope for the best.
And expect the worst.
We have to get help.
With no position he's a needle in a haystack.
What do you need?
Navy AWACS SLAR or
SAR 100k swath imaging.
You're gonna have to find somebody
at the Pentagon to get it.
Wait for me downstairs.
- I need to speak with him.
- Could you take a seat?
- Is he in?
- Yes.
Sorry. This can't wait.
Sir?
Can you hold on a minute?
What is it, Agent Scully?
I just received some very disturbing
information, sir. I need your help.
I'll call you back in five.
- You can't come rushing in here.
- I couldn't waste time explaining myself.
- Tell me what is so urgent.
- Mulder's done something incredibly rash.
- I can't.
- He may be lost at sea.
- You can't what?
- Help. There's nothing I can do for you.
- It isn't for me. It's for Mulder.
My hands are tied. I'm not
your direct superior now.
- Don't you wanna know what this is about?
- No, I don't. I don't even wanna hear it.
- Sir, this is about a man's life.
- I'm not allowed to have contact with you.
Any contact with you or Mulder.
She walked right past me, sir.
- You're out of line, Scully.
- No, sir, you're out of line.
I'm sorry, but I'm coming to you for help
and I've got nowhere else to go.
I would hope that after everything
you'd have the courtesy,
the decency, and not to mention the respect
to listen to what I have to say.
Now, all I need is information.
You don't have to do anything else.
Sir, if you know anybody at the Office of
Naval Intelligence it would be of great help.
I could lose my job. My pension.
I could even be subject to legal action.
Use your head, Scully. It'll save your ass.
Save your own ass, sir.
You'll save your head along with it.
Ouch!
Sorry.
Yes, sir. I'll get those files
and make that call.
- I need a word with AD Kersh.
- Sorry. He's not available.
Assistant Director Kersh,
may I have a moment?
- A moment for what?
- Uh, may I, sir? Thank you.
Sir, I need you to get me some information.
I am not at liberty to say why but I can
tell you it is of the utmost importance.
- Yes?
- I, uh...
Sorry, I shouldn't have come unannounced.
May I see what you were gonna
show me, Agent Scully?
Uh...
It... well, it's nothing.
Really.
Good.
What am I thinking? What am I thinking?
Sorry.
Come on, come on, come on.
Answer the phone, Mulder.
Answer the phone. Answer the phone.
The cellular customer you are trying
to reach is not responding.
Damn.
I want you to do me a favour. It is not
negotiable. Either you do it or I kill you.
- Are you OK?
- No, I'm not.
I'm a gun ready to go off, so don't test me
or think about trying to weasel me.
What is it that you need?
Navy AWACS SLAR 100k swath
south-southeast of Bermuda.
I am looking for a boat, maybe a ship.
- 1939 luxury liner.
- 1939?
Don't ask too many questions.
I don't care what you do.
I need that information and
I need it now. Are we clear?
Crystal.
Agent Spender? If you're not back in a hurry
I'll hunt you down and so help me God...
Right.
God.
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- (Cigarette Smoking Man) Agent Fowley?
Yes.
I was looking for Agent Spender.
I'm sorry. He's not here right now.
ls there something I can help with?
Yeah. Agent Scully just gave
the assistant director a piece of paper
with an intelligence system scribbled on it.
Yes?
- Yes, sir?
- Who is this?
(phone ringing)
- Agent Scully.
- I...
- I was sent to fetch you.
- I was waiting for Agent Spender. Uh...
I was supposed to pick up
a delivery from him.
Agent Spender is with
Assistant Director Kersh.
That rat bastard!
Stupid!
(phone rings)
Scully!
(crackling and interference)
Mulder, is that you?
No, I can't. I'm on an elevator.
Hold on. I'll be off in a s...
Hold on.
(distorted voice)
- Hello?
- Scully?
- No!
- (distorted voice)
I can't understand!
I can't...
- Was that you?
- Is it you?
I've been trying to reach you.
I got the information you needed.
- How?
- Don't even ask.
Sir, what you've done...
- ...could save Mulder's ass. I know.
- Thanks.
And if you ever ask me to break policy
I will have you written up
and tossed out of the FBI
for good. Understood?
Yes, sir.
Yes.
- Did you get it?
- Yeah.
Oi! American, right?
Saved your life, mate. Krauts don't want
no reason to bring you Yanks into the war.
- I got two words for you - Pearl Harbor.
- What?
After Poland, Hitler's off to Denmark,
Holland and France, with a few stopoffs.
The French all but roll over on us.
The Italians seize their opportunity and
the Japanese come through the back door.
It's a long bloody story with a happy ending.
We win?
You come out on the side
of history with help from us.
Not much to apologise
over the next 50 years,
except for maybe the Spice Girls.
Dann mal raus mit euch. Vorwérts.
Worauf wartet ihr? Mach schon. Los.
Well, according to our host
this'll be our new accommodations, lads.
You speak German.
What was that shouting about?
They got it in mind that we left America
carrying arms to England.
Are we?
Listen. She's drawing 16 feet at 81,000 tons.
We're making 21 knots at full power.
If we got munitions aboard this ship
they weigh but a few stone.
But the captain knew something.
He wouldn't give up the wheel.
The Nazis boarded us after
they intercepted a radio communication.
Some kind of codeword
they keep asking about.
Thor's Hammer.
Do you know what that is, mate?
Who goes there? I said who goes there?
Show your faces or
we'll bloody beat them to a stump.
Put your irons down.
It's your own crew, for God's sake.
- What you doing here?
- Having a cup of tea.
- What's it look like, you stupid swabbo?
- Then who's steering the boat?
Just some blokes who answer
to the name of Heil Hitler.
You ever been to Germany? They'll have
a special affection for the likes of you.
- Yeah, right.
- This ship can't go to Germany.
- Make up your mind, mate.
- I got news for you.
You're not carrying munitions.
It's something more deadly.
- Thor's Hammer.
- That isn't a weapon. It's a man.
A man who helped build a bomb
that'll win the war for whoever has it.
- You're telling me he's aboard this ship?
- I saw him. In the ballroom.
Was ist los?
Sein Name ist Thors Hammer.
Er hat einen Plan, eine Bombe zu bauen.
Auf Wiedersehen, mates.
What's wrong with you? Don't you know
there are spies everywhere?
Trust no one, man!
We've got to stop this ship! Now!
Hey, you! Who's in charge
of this engine room?
Hey, I'm talking to you! Shut her down,
man. We've got to scuttle her now.
- Put some piss in her, boys!
- You heard him! Kill the engines!
There's no other way, swabbo.
You can't get to Germany if you can't steer.
Me overriding her.
We steerin' a course for home.
You seen your compass? You can't
get to England going the wrong way.
We're not going to England.
We're going to Jamaica.
(cheers)
You'll steer her home, you ruffo.
To the home where she belongs!
Listen to me! You can't take this ship
to England. You'll never make it.
There's only one place she's going.
- Jamaica!
- You can't take the ship to Jamaica either.
The Germans will hunt you down
no matter what course you steer.
Hear now! Hear now! Hear now!
And who you be, boy?
- My name's Mulder.
- He wants to go back to America.
No, I don't. I want you to take the ship,
turn it back around the way you came.
- Bloody hell! We're halfway home!
- You've got to turn this ship around.
- And what's in that direction?
- The future.
Actually, the past.
- Oh, well, I'm convinced(!)
- I can explain it to you.
Du! Der Amerikaner!
Du kommst mit uns. Rauf hier. Mitkommen.
Turn this ship around!
Or Hitler rises, Germany wins
and your children will never
know what freedom is!
Halt's Maul jetzt.
Klappe! Weitergehen!
Links rum.
Na komm, mach schon.
Halt! Halt! Stehen bleiben!
Stehen bleiben oderich schieBe.
Aufstehen.
Mach schnell! Get up!
Er sagte...
Wir haben einen Mann an Bord,
einen Wissenschaftler,
der weiB, wie man eine Bombe macht,
die den Krieg gewinnen wird.
Frag ihn, wer dieser Mann ist.
There's a scientist on board who can
make a bomb. Who is this man?
I don't know.
Waffe bereit!
Sag ihm, wir werden
einen Passagier umbringen,
furjede falsche Antwon'.
You will answer the question
or we will begin killing passengers.
Which one is the scientist?
I don't know.
ErschieB ihn.
(gunshot)
Frag ihn, wie viele Personen
er sterben Iésst.
How many lives are you willing to sacrifice?
None.
Then you have the answer?
Er weigert sich ihn zu nennen.
SchieB noch mal!
(gun clicks)
(gunshot)
Stop!
He has no answers. You're killing innocent
people to learn that he knows nothing.
- Shut up! Shut up and move away.
- Listen to me, you little weasel!
(Cigarette Smoking Man) Wir haben
unseren néchsten Passagier, eine Dame.
Richte die Waffe auf sie.
ErschieB sie, wenn er
die Frage nicht beantwortet.
Answer the question.
I'll answer the question.
(Cigarette Smoking Man)
Beantworte die Frage.
That man is the scientist.
(Frohike) Hey, Scully. Scully, you're
not gonna believe this. Get up here.
(Scully) What?
(Frohike) The sky just cleared
and there it was.
(Scully) Is it the Queen Anne?
(Byers) That's her.
- (Scully) I don't believe it.
- (Frohike) Seeing is believing.
(Scully) They've got power.
(Langly) Maybe Mulder's already on board.
(Scully) Let's hope he is.
- You're lying.
- He's telling the truth.
Shut up! Who is the scientist?
I told you. This man is the scientist.
Untersuchen!
- Frag ihn, wie der Mann heiBt.
- What is the man's name?
John Brown. Ask me again
and I'll knock you down.
- What's his name?
- Puddintame.
- Ask me again and I'll tell you the same.
- (man) Wait! Don't shoot.
- I'm the scientist.
- This man's a liar.
I'm the scientist.
Please, tell the truth
before someone else has to die.
- I don't know him.
- Don't listen to her.
She is travelling with me to protect me.
She works for the OSS.
Fuhrt diesen Mann ab.
(speaks German)
That's great.
I don't see you did any better.
ErschieB sie zuerst.
ErschieB alle.
What did he say?
- I think I know what he said.
- You learn fast.
(engines stop)
- What's happening?
- The engine shut down.
- (Mulder) Hey!
- (Scully) What?
- Come with me.
- Why should I?
Cos you're the only one
who can save this ship.
Come on.
Stehen bleiben!
Stehen bleiben oderich erschieBe Sie.
Hénde hoch. Hinter Ihren Kopf.
- Machen Sie's!
- Now what, Einstein?
Machen Sie's!
(gunshot)
God bless America.
Now get your asses out of here.
(SCUIIy) Byers'?
Langlv?
Frohike?
Come on. Come on.
There you guys are.
- What are you doing?
- Telling you how to save the ship.
I can't stay. I gotta get back to history.
- What?
- You gotta rescue it. Wait, listen to me.
The ship's been caught
in something called the Devil's Triangle.
Some kind of time warp.
Are you crazy?
Einstein predicts the theoretical possibility.
He also predicts an atomic weapon
to destroy the world.
Yeah? So what?
If you don't go back and convince the crew
to head back into the Devil's Triangle,
everything Einstein predicted will become
true, except for the outcome of history.
So if I don't turn this ship around...
In all likelihood, I won't exist.
And neither will you.
So in case we never meet again...
I was expecting the left.
Hey!
(SCU/ly) Mulder?
Mulder, it's me.
- Where am I?
- You're in a hospital.
- Oh!
- Lie Still.
I feel... like hell.
I don't blame you. You've been
through the wringer, I'd say.
- What happened to me?
- You did something incredibly stupid.
- What did I do?
- You went looking for a ship, Mulder.
In the Bermuda Triangle.
- Say that again?
- (Frohike) Gilligan awakes.
- You were there.
- Hm?
- You were there, Scully.
- He's delirious.
- And he was there too.
- Right, me and my dog, Toto.
- No, you were there with the Nazis.
- Will you settle down? It's an order.
- Not that he takes orders.
- You saved the world, Scully.
- Yeah. You're right. I did.
- What kind of drugs is he on?
- I want some.
- No, the Queen Anne. I found it.
You were there with Thor's Hammer. I told
you to turn the ship around, then I jumped.
Yeah, I bet you did.
The boat that you were on
was busted into a million pieces.
And as for the Queen Anne,
it was nothing more than a ghost ship.
No, no, no. You and lwere
on that ship, Scully, in 1939.
Get some rest, Mulder,
cos when you get out of here,
I'm gonna kick your butt, by God.
I would never have seen you again.
But you believed me.
In your dreams.
Mulder, I want you to close your eyes,
and I want you to think to yourself
"There's no place like home".
Mm.
Hey, Scully.
Yes?
I love you.
Oh, brother.
Visiontext Subtitles: Abigail Smith
(Child) I made this!